- HEY, GUYS.
READY FOR SOME
MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- ( laughing )
I'VE FINALLY SURPASSED
THE OLD MAN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( coughing )
- ( coughs )
- WHAT THE-- NO WAY.
IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW IN THE HELL
ARE YOU ALL STILL ALIVE?
- ( All speaking )
- ( groans )
- LEVY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- BUT WHAT ABOUT NATSU?
IS HE OKAY?
- ( pants )
- LOOKS JUST FINE TO ME.
- I HIT THEM WITH
SO MUCH MAGIC ENERGY.
- Fried: THE OTHER GUILD MEMBERS
AND THE CITIZENS OF MAGNOLIA
REMAIN UNHARMED.
- Laxus: FRIED.
- LOOKS LIKE YOUR
SPELL DIDN'T WORK.
NOT A SINGLE PERSON
WAS KILLED.
- BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I CAST THE FAIRY LAW SPELL
PERFECTLY.
- MAYBE SO, BUT YOU'RE TRUE
FEELINGS HAVE BETRAYED YOU.
YOU'VE INHERITED MORE THAN
STRENGTH FROM YOUR GRANDFATHER.
DEEP DOWN, YOU ALSO HAVE
THE MASTER'S HEART.
WHETHER YOU'D
ADMIT IT OR NOT,
IT'S EVIDENT THAT YOU CARE
FOR YOUR COMRADES.
THE FAIRY LAW SPELL
ONLY AFFECTS THOSE
THE CASTER SEES
AS THEIR ENEMY.
SINCE NO ONE WAS HURT,
WE KNOW HOW YOU TRULY FEEL.
- HIS MAGIC COULD
SEE INTO HIS HEART.
AND THAT'S WHY
WE'RE STILL HERE.
- YOU CAN TRY TO HIDE
YOUR FEELINGS, LAXUS,
BUT YOUR MAGIC WILL
ALWAYS REVEAL THE TRUTH
WITHIN YOUR HEART.
- NO, THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
THE TRUTH IS ANYONE WHO WOULD
EVER DARE STAND IN MY WAY
IS MY ENEMY!
- THIS HAS GONE
ON LONG ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO GO SEE THE MASTER
BEFORE HE'S GONE.
- ( grunts )
LET THE OLD MAN DIE
FOR ALL I CARE.
HE'S NOTHING TO ME.
HE MAY BE FAMILY,
BUT I'M STRONGER!
- SUCH POWER.
- WHO DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE?
YOU'RE NOT
STRONGER THAN GRAMPS.
YOU COULDN'T EVEN
PULL OFF FAIRY LAW.
YOU MAY BE HIS GRANDSON,
BUT YOU'RE NO BETTER
THAN THE REST OF US.
DON'T YOU KNOW BLOOD TIES
DON'T MATTER?
'CAUSE EVERYONE IN THE GUILD
IS SUPPOSED TO
BE CONSIDERED FAMILY.
- THAT'S JUST A LIE.
BLOOD TIES DO MATTER.
- YOU'VE BEEN
A MEMBER LONG ENOUGH
TO KNOW BETTER THAN THAT.
IF YOU THINK THAT MAKES YOU
ABOVE EVERYONE ELSE
IN THE GUILD,
YOU'RE WRONG!
- AND YOU'RE DEAD!
HOW DARE YOU CHALLENGE ME!
- I'M GONNA STOP YOU, LAXUS.
I WON'T LET YOU GET
YOUR HANDS ON FAIRY TAIL.
IT'S OUR HOME!
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA LET YOU DESTROY IT.
- WHY WON'T YOU JUST DIE?!
- FACE IT ALREADY.
IT'S OVER.
- NATSU!
- Natsu: WHY WON'T YOU
JUST GIVE UP THE FIGHT?
IT JUST DOESN'T
BELONG TO YOU.
IT NEVER WILL!
- OH YEAH?!
LIGHTNING DRAGON!
DEMOLITION FIST!
DIDN'T THE OLD MAN
EVER TEACH YOU
TO RESPECT YOUR ELDERS, BOY?
- NO WAY.
HE CAN STILL FIGHT?
- NATSU, PLEASE
BE CAREFUL.
- THAT WAS YOUR
LAST MISTAKE, KID.
NOW I'M GONNA
OBLITERATE YOU!
- THAT SPELL, DON'T DO IT!
THAT MUCH MAGIC ENERGY
COULD KILL HIM!
- ( laughs )
- LIGHTNING DRAGON!
HEAVENWARD HALBERD!
- NATSU!
- ( cries )
- GAJEEL!
- WHAT THE-- WHAT HAPPENED?
DID HE USE HIMSELF
AS A LIGHTNING ROD?
- GET HIM!
- ( grunts )
-  DAMN.
HE'S STILL ALIVE.
FIRE DRAGON...
- ( roars )
- IRON FIST!
TALON!
WING ATTACK!
SWORD HORN!
FLAME ELBOW!
- HE REALLY IS AMAZING.
HIS MAGIC IS SO POWERFUL.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE IT CAN BREAK
THROUGH A DRAGON'S SCALES
AND SHATTER IT'S SPIRIT.
- DRAGON SLAYER SECRET ARTS.
- FLAME LOTUS!
EXPLODING FLAME BLADE!
- ( grunts, groans )
( screams )
- Fried: HE DID IT.
HE BEAT LAXUS.
- ( roars )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE, GRANDINE?
- PAYING A VISIT
TO AN OLD FRIEND.
- MIGHT I REMIND YOU
YOU'RE FORBIDDEN TO COME HERE?
DO NOT INTERFERE.
- I SHOULD TELL YOU THAT
THE CHILD IS BEING RECKLESS.
HE REMINDS ME
OF SOMEONE ELSE I KNOW.
HIS STREAK OF GOOD LUCK
IS SURE TO RUN OUT EVENTUALLY.
IN WHICH CASE,
HE COULD END UP DEAD.
- BE GONE!
YOU ARE NOT TO MEDDLE
IN THE HUMAN'S AFFAIRS!
DO SO AND YOU WILL ANGER ME,
THE MIGHTY IGNEEL!
- I NEVER SHOULD
HAVE MENTIONED IT.
THERE'S NO POINT IN WORRYING
WHEN WE CAN'T
CHANGE THE OUTCOME.
ALL WE CAN DO IS HAVE FAITH
THAT THE HUMANS
HAVE THE STRENGTH TO PREVAIL.
YOU KNOW, ZEREF IS--
NEVER MIND.
I'VE SAID ENOUGH.
- ( townspeople chatter )
- Man #1: AWW MAN,
THE FANTASIA PARADE
WON'T HAPPEN
UNTIL TOMORROW NIGHT.
- Woman #1:
YEAH, I HEARD IT'S CAUSE
THE MASTER IS SICK.
- Man #2: IS HE GOING TO RETIRE?
- Woman #2: WHOA, WHO DO YOU
THINK THE NEXT MASTER WILL BE?
- Man #3: WELL, LAXUS
WOULD MAKE THE MOST SENSE.
- Man #4: BUT HE'S SUCH A JERK.
- Man #5: YEAH.
I REALLY HOPE
THEY DON'T PUT HIM IN CHARGE.
- Man #5: I'VE KNOWN HIM SINCE
HE WAS JUST A BOY.
AND NOW HE MIGHT BE
THE NEW MASTER.
IF I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
AN OLD MAN BEFORE,
I SURE DO NOW.
- Erza: THANKS TO
PORLYUSICA'S HELP,
THE MASTER'S GOING TO
PULL THROUGH JUST FINE.
SO DON'T WORRY.  HE'LL BE
BACK TO WORK IN NO TIME.
- ( cheering )
- THANK GOODNESS.
I GOT TO ADMIT I WAS GETTING
A LITTLE WORRIED.
- AH, COME ON,
IT'LL TAKE MORE THAN THAT
TO MAKE GRAMPS
KICK THE BUCKET.
WELL, HE ISN'T AS YOUNG
AS HE USED TO BE.
SO ANY ADDED STRESS
TO HIS HEART
COULD SIGNIFICANTLY
AFFECT HIS HEALTH.
LET'S BE ON OUR
BEST BEHAVIOR, OKAY?
- All: AYE, SIR!
- I DON'T KNOW IF
IT'S SUCH A GOOD IDEA
TO DO THE FANTASIA PARADE
AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED.
- BUT THE MASTER
WANTS US TO DO IT.
BESIDES, IT'S THE PERFECT WAY
TO CHEER EVERYONE UP
AFTER ALL THAT MESS.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT YOU ALL HAVE IN STORE
FOR THE PARADE.
- YEAH?
- YOU'RE GONNA BE IN IT WITH US,
LITTLE LADY.
- ( gasps )
- YOU'RE A MEMBER, RIGHT?
- WELL, YEAH, I AM,
BUT I'M SO NEW,
I DIDN'T THINK
I'D BE IN THE PARADE.
- I WAS EXPECTING A LITTLE MORE
EXCITEMENT FROM HER.
- SHE LOOKS UPSET.
- ISN'T SHE THE CUTEST?
- A LOT OF MEMBERS WERE INJURED
FIGHTING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
SO ANYONE WHO'S NOT HURT
HAS TO PARTICIPATE.
- DOES THAT MEAN
I'M GONNA BE IN IT TOO?
- WELL, YEAH, WE NEED
ALL THE PEOPLE WE CAN GET.
ESPECIALLY SINCE WE'RE NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO USE THOSE TWO.
- OH YEAH.
- SCREW YOU
AND YOUR PARADE.
- ( muffled response )
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT HE JUST SAID?
- KNOWING HIM, IT WAS
PROBABLY SOMETHING STUPID.
- COME ON, HOW'RE YOU GONNA
BE PART OF THE ACTION?
YOU'RE OUT.
- ( muffled response )
- THAT'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT, BRO.
WHAT THE HECK
IS YOUR PROBLEM?!
- I WONDER HOW GAJEEL
CAN UNDERSTAND HIM.
- WELL, IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE
HE'S JUST AS STUPID AS NATSU IS.
- Lucy: THAT WAS HARSH.
YOU'VE GOT A SERIOUS
MEAN STREAK IN YOU, CAT.
- ( giggles )
- Erza: IT'S GOOD TO SEE
EVERYONE GETTING ALONG AGAIN.
ESPECIALLY AFTER WE WERE FORCED
TO FIGHT AGAINST ONE ANOTHER.
- ( footsteps approach )
- ( gasping )
- Macao: LAXUS.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WHERE'S THE OLD MAN?
- WE AIN'T TELLING.
- YOU THINK YOU CAN
JUST WALTZ IN HERE AND
ASK TO SEE THE MASTER?
- ( shouting )
- YEAH, GET OUT OF HERE.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
- ( shouting )
- GUYS, STOP IT.
- QUIET, EVERYONE.
- Levy: ERZA.
- THE MASTER'S IN THE INFIRMARY.
- ARE YOU NUTS?
- ( whispering )
- ( muffled speech )
- NATSU.
( muffled speech continues )
( panting )
- WHAT'D HE SAY?
- CAN YOU INTERPRET PLEASE?
- HE SAID, "NEXT TIME,
IT AIN'T GONNA
BE TWO AGAINST ONE.
I'LL JUST BE ME AND YOU
FACE-TO-FACE.
AND I SWEAR I AIN'T
GONNA LOSE TO YOU AGAIN."
OR SOMETHING.
- Lucy: WAIT A SECOND.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS BEAT HIM.
- Gajeel: NO, I'D SAY
IT WAS MORE LIKE A DRAW.
- HUH?
- LOOK WHAT HE DID TO US.
IF HE HAD BEEN AROUND DURING
THE PHANTOM BATTLE,
I'D BE SIX FEET UNDER RIGHT NOW.
- ( muffled grumbles )
( muffled speech )
( shaky breath )
( sighs )
- Erza: SHOW'S OVER, GUYS.
LET'S GET READY
FOR THE FANTASIA PARADE.
- ( cheering )
( chattering )
( distant cheers )
- THEY'RE A ROWDY BUNCH,
AREN'T THEY?
- LAXUS.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND
THE SERIOUSNESS
OF WHAT YOU HAVE DONE.
LOOK ME IN THE EYES,
YOUNG MAN.
FAIRY TAIL IS A PLACE...
WHERE FRIENDS CAN GATHER,
WIZARDS CAN FIND WORK,
AND CHILDREN WHO HAVE
NO KIN TO CALL THEIR OWN
CAN FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
PART OF A FAMILY.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING
THAT CAN BE OWNED.
IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT EACH MEMBER
NOT ONLY BE LOYAL,
BUT ALSO TRUSTWORTHY.
OTHERWISE, NO BONDS
WILL BE FORMED
AND THE ENTIRE GUILD
WILL EVENTUALLY FALL APART.
YOUR ACTIONS HAVE PROVEN
THAT YOU LACK BOTH
OF THOSE QUALITIES.
AND YOU THREATENED
THE LIVES OF YOUR COMRADES.
THAT'S UNFORGIVABLE.
- I'M SORRY, SIR.
HONESTLY, I NEVER MEANT
TO HURT THE GUILD.
I JUST WANTED TO
MAKE IT STRONGER.
- ( sighs )
I SWEAR,
YOU'RE JUST AS
HIGH-STRUNG AS I AM.
YOU'D BETTER TRY TO RELAX
OR YOU'LL END UP
IN HERE WITH ME.
TAKE SOME TIME
TO SMELL THE ROSES.
IF YOU DO, YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE THINGS
YOU COULDN'T SEE BEFORE.
AND YOU'LL HEAR THINGS
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO HEAR.
LIFE CAN BE A LOT OF FUN
IF YOU ALLOW IT TO BE.
OVER THE YEARS,
I HAVE WATCHED YOU GROW
INTO THE MAN THAT YOU ARE TODAY.
WHERE DID WE GO WRONG?
WHAT LESSON DID YOU NOT LEARN?
BUT THE PAST IS THE PAST.
I AM LEFT NOW
WITH ONLY ONE CHOICE.
LAXUS...
YOU ARE HEREBY EXPELLED
FROM FAIRY TAIL.
- I UNDERSTAND.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING...
GRANDPA.
- ( sniffles )
- YOU TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
OKAY, OLD MAN.
- ( cries )
PLEASE JUST GO.
- NO! YOU MUST BE JOKING!
WHY WOULD HE KICK YOU OUT
AND NOT THE REST OF US?
- Bixlow: YEAH, I MEAN, WE'RE
JUST AS GUILTY AS YOU ARE.
- Tommen: JUST AS GUILTY.
TOTALLY GUILTY.
GUILTY ALRIGHT.
YOU BET YOU'RE GUILTY.
- GUESS THE OLD MAN
DOESN'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
- WELL, IF YOU'RE LEAVING
THE GUILD, THEN I'M LEAVING TOO.
- WHY SHOULD WE STICK AROUND
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE HERE?
- YOU GUYS CAN BE SUCH
A PAIN IN THE NECK.
I MEAN, CAN'T YOU JUST SAY
GOOD-BYE AND BE DONE WITH IT?
- Fried: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WE'RE AT FAULT TOO.
SO WHY ARE YOU
TAKING ALL THE BLAME?
- YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG,
MY FRIENDS.
YOU CAN SAY
WHATEVER YOU WANT,
BUT I KNOW YOU GUYS
ARE MUCH MORE ATTACHED
TO THIS GUILD
THAN I COULD EVER BE.
- IF WE TALK TO THE MASTER,
MAYBE WE CAN CHANGE HIS MIND.
- YEAH, NATSU AND
GRAY RESPECT YOU.
SO THEY'LL PROBABLY
GO WITH US.
HE LOVES THOSE GUYS.
I'M SURE HE'LL LISTEN TO THEM.
- ARE YOU REALLY LEAVING?
- TAKE CARE OF YOURSELVES.
- LAXUS, WAIT!
- HEY, YOU CAN'T JUST
LEAVE US BEHIND.
WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO
THE THUNDER LEGION?
- ( cries )
- MAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
- I'M SURE WE'LL
MEET AGAIN, LAXUS.
- Hades:
EXCELLENT WORK, ULTEAR.
WHAT BECAME OF JELLAL?
- TO BE HONEST,
I COULDN'T CARE LESS.
- THE POOR FELLOW
NEVER EVEN HAD A CLUE
THAT YOU WERE THE ONE
PULLING THE STRINGS.
HUH, PATHETIC.
- HMM, HE MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
THE BRIGHTEST MAN,
BUT HE WAS ADORABLE.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT IN ALL THOSE YEARS,
HE NEVER REALIZED
THAT I WAS PRETENDING
TO BE THE SPIRIT
OF LORD ZEREF.
- YOUR ABILITIES SET THE STAGE
FOR GREAT THINGS,
THE MAGIC COUNCIL IN TURMOIL,
THE ETHERION FIRING.
OUR PLAN
IS COMING TO FRUITION.
- I HAD HOPED THAT WHILE JELLAL
WAS RUNNING AMOK,
YOU'D BE ABLE TO
MOVE ABOUT FREELY.
- ONE OF THE KEYS
NEEDED TO UNLOCK THE SEAL
IS NOW IN MY POSSESSION.
- IS THAT SO?
THAT'S GOOD, MASTER HADES.
( chuckles )
I'M SORRY THINGS
HAD TO END THIS WAY,
MY DEAR JELLAL.
- ( fireworks pop )
- ( cheering )
( cheering, chatter )
( catcalls )
( chattering )
( cheering )
- ( roars )
- ( gasps )
( cheering )
- Boys: HUH?!
- ( cheering )
( surprised murmurs )
- AYE.
- ( inhales deeply )
- ( cheers )
- ( coughs )
- HMM.
- Gajeel: HEY, MASTER.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
IN THE PARADE, GAJEEL?
- I DON'T LIKE BEING
IN THE SPOTLIGHT.
- THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
YOU'RE MISTER SHOO-BEE-DOO-BA.
- HERE, THIS IS FOR YOU.
SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG.
BUT I FINALLY
TRACKED DOWN YOUR SON
MASTER IVAN.
- GOOD WORK, MY BOY.
I'M SORRY
IT WAS SO DANGEROUS.
- NO PROB.  I CAN HANDLE IT.
IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF FUN.
AND THAT GUY HAS NO IDEA
THAT I'M A DOUBLE AGENT.
- THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
WE CAN'T LET HIM
DO AS HE PLEASES.
- Man #1: YOU READY, MASTER?
IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME.
- SORRY, BUT
MY PUBLIC NEEDS ME.
- Woman: IT'S THE MASTER.
- Man #2: IS THAT REALLY HIM?
OH WOW.
- Man #3: HE SURE IS WEARING A
FANCY OUTFIT, HUH?
- Man #2: I'D SAY IT'S
MORE FUNKY THAN FANCY.
- I LIKE IT.
- WHY'S HE ACTING SO GOOFY?♪
- Young Laxus:
BUT HOW COME...
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE IN
THE FANTASIA PARADE THIS YEAR?
- 'CAUSE THIS
IS YOUR BIG MOMENT.
BUT I'LL BE WATCHING YOU
FROM THE SIDELINES.
- WHEN I LOOK INTO THE CROWD,
HOW WILL I FIND YOU?
- FORGET ABOUT ME.
TODAY, YOU'RE THE STAR.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
OH, I KNOW.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE PARADE,
I'LL DO THIS!
YOU COULD SEE THAT, RIGHT?
- YOU'LL RAISE YOUR HAND?
- IT'S A MESSAGE.
WHEN YOU SEE ME HOLDING UP
MY HAND LIKE THIS,
IT MEANS EVEN
IF I CAN'T SEE YOU,
I'M LOOKING YOUR WAY.
- THAT'S MY BOY.
- Young Laxus:
BE SURE TO LOOK FOR IT, OKAY?
- ( humming )
- GRANDPA.
- Makarov: I MAY NOT
BE ABLE TO SEE YOU.
THERE MAY BE HUNDREDS
OF MILES BETWEEN US,
BUT I'LL ALWAYS
BE LOOKING YOUR WAY.
I'LL BE WATCHING
OVER YOU FOREVER.
I PROMISE.
- Laxus: I KNOW.
THANK YOU, GRANDPA.
- Natsu: THE PARTY'S
JUST GETTING STARTED.
( laughs )
I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW.
- AYE AYE, SIR.
- Natsu: OKAY, GUYS,
WHO'S PROUD TO BE A MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL?
- Members: YEEHAW!
( laughing )
- I KNOW I'M JUST A ROOKIE
AND I'VE GOT
A LONG WAY TO GO,
BUT I'M GONNA WORK HARD
TO BECOME
AS AWESOME A WIZARD
AS THE OTHERS.
FAIRY TAIL IS
THE GREATEST GUILD EVER.
- IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL,
YOUR FACE'LL GET STUCK
IN THAT GOOFY GRIN.
- NO WAY! NOT MY PRETTY FACE!
- I WAS JUST WARNING YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET ALL
BENT OUT OF SHAPE ABOUT IT.
- Lucy: WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
YOU SAID MY FACE
WAS GONNA GET STUCK.
GEEZ, WE FINALLY HAVE
A TOUCHING ENDING
AND YOU HAVE TO GO
AND RUIN IT.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- DID YOU HEAR THE NEWS?
A REPORTER FROM
"SORCERER WEEKLY" MAGAZINE
IS COMING TO
VISIT FAIRY TAIL.
- MAN, I HATE THOSE
SLEAZY REPORTERS.
THEY ALWAYS MAKE ME OUT
TO BE THE BAD GUY.
I'LL GIVE 'EM
A PIECE OF MY MIND.
- ACTUALLY, I THINK THEY
JUST TELL IT LIKE IT IS.
CAN YOU PROMISE ME THAT
YOU WON'T CAUSE THE GUILD
ANY TROUBLE? PLEASE.
- I PROMISE I'LL BE
ON MY BEST BEHAVIOR.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: YOU SEE WHAT WE DID
WITH THE TITLE THERE?
THAT'S WHAT'S CALLED
FORESHADOWING.
- OH YEAH, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- AH, YOU'LL FIND OUT
NEXT TIME.
OR WILL YOU?