[LARCADE]
I love that look on your face.
It's rare to see someone
caught between
defiance and resignation.
[yells]
[LARCADE]
Fear not.
For eventually this pain will
give way to ultimate pleasure.
You were fierce earlier.
And you referred to the
magic I wield as "vulgar."
I concede that may be
true to a certain degree.
But if you look, you'll
find there's love in it.
It allows you to die
without feeling any pain.
[LARCADE]
May your spirit of pure white
into the heavens take flight.
Kagura, no!
Enjoy it for now.
Your pleasure will
become so intense
you'll be begging
for it to stop.
[gasps]
No!
And now, your death will
be filled with pure bliss.
These two have serious injuries,
but they should pull through.
Luckily, I was able to
shrink their wounds.
That's great. Thanks a lot.
[PORLYUSICA]
And if it weren't for Wendy,
we could've lost Juvia.
The main concern is with Natsu.
Poor guy.
Earlier, I could shrink
the mass inside of him,
but my magic seems to've
lost its effect on it.
Whatever that is,
I'm not powerful enough
to counteract it.
That's quite alarming.
Considering we've seen you
shrink an entire island
down to the size of a pebble.
I wonder what could
possibly be that resistant.
It boggles the mind.
He was immune to the
time-stopping spell.
And flew into a violent
rage when it was cast.
I hate to admit it, but I'm
completely at a loss.
[DIMARIA]
He's a demon.
That's the only way
to truly describe him.
[HAPPY]
A demon. E.N.D.
You're wrong about
Natsu! That's a lie!
And you believe you know him
to his very core, do you?
I know him way better
than you ever will,
I can guarantee you that.
How naive. You can never
truly know a person.
Even so-called "friends"
have things
they keep hidden away
from each other.
Right, Randi?
I mean, Natsu...
he has outbursts,
and he's kinda hard to
work with sometimes,
but I have no doubt
that he's been honest
about who he really
is deep down.
She's totally fallen for him.
Seems like it.
Oh, grow up, would ya?
He's practically the
reason I was able
to join Fairy Tail
in the first place.
I'm grateful.
[gasps]
What's happening?
I've never seen someone
just give off smoke.
Natsu, no!
I'm afraid it might be related
to that strange mass
growing inside of him.
Wake up, Natsu!
[LUCY]
He's cold!
Natsu, come on! Say something!
[HAPPY]
Please!
[EVERGREEN]
Natsu!
[CARLA]
Open your eyes!
[LUCY]
He's not responding!
Natsu! Natsu!
Where the hell am I?
Wait, is somebody there?
It's just me, Natsu.
What do you want?
Calm down, please.
All of this is taking place
inside your subconscious.
I don't have to
listen to this crap!
[ZEREF] My point is,
I'm not really here with you.
Wait, so this is like
a dream or somethin'?
In a way.
While we're here,
I'd like to ask a favor.
Do you think you could please
call me big brother now?
[NATSU]
Hell no!
It's the end for you.
You will die at any moment.
But before it's completely over,
I wanted the chance to fill in
some of the blanks
in your memory.
Say what?
[ZEREF] There's quite a bit to
go over before the year 777,
when you awoke.
I was living with Igneel.
[ZEREF]
Before even that time.
[ZEREF] We had a quiet, peaceful
family life in a small village.
[ZEREF] Our mother and father
were kind and loving.
[ZEREF] But that idyllic life
was shattered in an instant
when dragons destroyed our home.
Our mother and
father were killed,
and you perished right
alongside them.
[gasps]
[ZEREF]
I vowed to bring you back.
And after many years of
research and hard work.
That became a reality.
You were reincarnated as
E.N.D., the ultimate demon.
I realize I've shared that story
with you before to some degree.
You refused to learn
to talk or read.
I was at my wit's end, so I
consulted my friend Igneel.
I left you in his care.
He'd teach you many things,
but most importantly,
you'd learn Dragon Slayer Magic
so you could one day
defeat Acnologia.
For that same purpose,
Metalicana raised Gajeel,
Weisslogia raised Sting,
Skiadrum raised Rogue,
and Grandeeney raised
little Wendy Marvel.
But it seems your memories
of this period are a bit fuzzy.
Perhaps the Dragon Soul
technique is to blame.
Do you recall when you
first met Gajeel?
You were always quarreling
over something.
And countless times,
Wendy would erupt in tears
as she begged you to get along.
[GRANDEENEY]
She has such a caring soul.
I'm sure when the
others join them,
they'll all become
great friends.
[ZEREF] Sting and Rogue were
about the same age as Wendy.
They looked up to you and
Gajeel like big brothers.
[STING] Our dragon parents
would get together
a few times every year.
Luckily, they'd always let
us tag along with them
and have some fun.
[NATSU]
Sting!
To be honest, I don't
remember a thing.
Not from around
that time, at least.
Wait a sec. What the hell
are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be fighting?
[STING]
I'm not actually Sting.
I'm more like an illusion of
him that your mind created,
or something like that.
Just a familiar face to guide
you through your memories.
Seriously?
Yep.
In the real world, I'm out there
fighting the Alvarez army.
Where did Zeref go?
[STING] Well, don't forget
we're inside your mind, Natsu.
I imagine you subconsciously
replaced him with me.
You're not makin'
any sense, man.
[STING]
That's all right. Follow me.
We can find the answer together.
To what?
Don't you wanna know
what that thing
growing inside you actually is?
Well, thanks to Fried's help,
I was able to get this far.
I'm going to search for Laxus.
Good luck!
Where's Rogue and Lector?
I hope they're okay.
Wait, that smell!
Don't give up. Please.
Try to hang in there.
[FROSCH groans]
[YUKINO] I can hardly
even think right now.
Sting, you gotta help us.
I know you're out
there! We need you!
[ALL gasp]
Sorry I'm late, you guys!
Oh, you made it!
I knew you'd come
for us, buddy!
Yay!
What's goin' on here?
Looks to me like you've
been givin' my guild members
a hard time!
What a surprise.
Seems yet another fool
has decided to join us.
If you truly want to
hurt me, then try harder.
Be careful, Sting!
Don't let that touch you!
[STING]
What is this?
It tastes kinda funky,
but it feels good,
in some weird way.
[laughs]
[STING]
White magic has no effect on me.
After all, I am the
White Dragon Slayer.
What's your deal?
Something pisses me off.
To make it worse,
you smell like Natsu.
Just who in the hell
are you, anyway?
Why do you and Natsu
have the same scent?
Well, according to him,
his last name is Dragneel,
just like Natsu.
He's told us a lot of things,
but I'm not sure we can
believe a single word of it.
He said that he's Zeref's son
and Natsu is Zeref's
younger brother.
Huh? That doesn't
make any sense to me.
I'm having a hard time
following it, too.
Hold on. It doesn't add up
with the way this guy smells.
If that's true, he and Natsu
having the same scent is weird.
[STING] I mean, I could sorta
see if he smelled like Zeref,
but Nastu and Zeref don't
really give off the same odor.
Everyone's got their own scent.
It's not genetic or anything.
But not this guy. He smells
exactly like Natsu.
Things are not so simple.
One could say Natsu is
Zeref's child like me.
What did I tell you?
Light magic and white magic
aren't gonna work on me!
[STING]
Holy Ray!
Holy Nova!
You're a more capable
foe than I'd realized.
But still...
[LARCADE]
Famished Soul!
[stomach growls]
Huh?
What's wrong, Sting?
The hunger you feel will
be impossible to endure.
[stomach growling]
[STING] Ugh. Oh, man.
I'm starving all of a sudden.
[chuckles]
[STING yells]
Stay strong, buddy!
I'm tryin'.
You can beat this guy.
Just hang in there!
You got this!
Come on, Sting!
You look so freakin' tasty!
[LECTOR]
Whoa! What? Sting, it's me!
[YUKINO] Master Sting!
What's come over you?
[KAGURA] Hey! Don't you dare
look at me like that!
Yes. Go and eat your fill.
[LECTOR]
Ow! Sting! Cut it out!
It's Lector! I'm your
friend, not your food!
[STING] I need meat!
My belly is crying!
Come to your senses!
Yukino?
So hungry. I can't
take it anymore.
I feel like I'm gonna
starve to death.
Oh, please. Save me some.
Hey, Rogue. Are you
still able to move?
I can get around somewhat.
I think I've taken
too much damage
to do anything beyond that.
[MINERVA]
I feel the same.
It's like my resources are gone.
This battle has taken nearly all
the strength I had left in me.
And we can probably
assume the others
have had their powers
drained as well.
Which means Sting and
Yukino are in trouble.
Whoever cast that spell
is quite powerful, indeed.
M'lady, are you able to
determine their location?
I can definitely sense
their power from here.
Seems to be coming
from that way.
Wouldn't be very much of
a journey to reach them.
You shouldn't go alone,
I can come with you.
Please stay. I believe
you should remain here.
I can go!
You've taken quite a bit more
damage than I have today.
In the event that
something happens to me,
it'd be better for our side
you if were to stay behind
and avoid the fight.
[LARCADE] The world of man
is filled with desires.
May you devour each other
and meet your ruin.
Everybody is super
hungry and I am, too.
But I think I'm gonna
wait a little bit
for Rogue to come back
so we can eat together.
I know you're dying of
starvation, ol' pal...
...so if this is the only
thing that'll save you...
I gotta do what I gotta do!
[STING] Sorry, ladies. I don't
have any other choice!
[YUKINO, KAGURA grunt]
[STING]
Sorry, Frosch!
[FROSCH groans]
[STING] This is the
only way I can think of
to fight my appetite!
That so?
But how do you plan to stave off
those crippling hunger pangs?
I'm just gonna have to eat you!
Have you forgotten how weak
this hunger has made you?
How could I forget? But still--!
There's no point in trying.
I'm Sabertooth's Master.
I gotta save my guild!
[LARCADE]
Hm. Never heard of them before.
Why would you bother getting
involved in such a fight
if you're not a member
of Fairy Tail?
Because their guild
needs our help right now
and that's what allies
do for each other!
[STING] Because they helped
us change for the better!
And because I owe it to Natsu!
Don't agonize over owing him.
His spirit will be
free from concern,
once he's been released
from this world.
I have taken on the
responsibility of killing him
with my own hands.
What the--?
M'lady's Territory spell!
Territory. That's
space-swapping magic.
Yukino!
Oh. I didn't see you before.
What are you doing?
Cut that out this instant!
I just can't help myself.
You look so yummy.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm not some sort
of dinner entrée!
Please, stop!
Wondered where you were.
I don't have enough strength
left to fight alongside you.
But m'lady sent me for
delivery, so eat me!
Say what? You mean--
[ROGUE]
You're hungry, aren't you?
So I want you to consume
the rest of my magic power!
But I can't eat a
different type of magic;
it's not gonna work.
Might as well try
since I'm starving!
There are three primary
desires that drive humans.
First one is sex.
Then there's food.
They're all eventually
followed by sleep.
[LARCADE] That is the final
desire I shall grant you.
The gift of sleep.
To be more precise, what I
offer is eternal slumber.
I've heard about
enough of your crap!
And I hate the way you smell!
It's burning up the
hair in my nostrils!
The fact that a weak,
insignificant person
has the gall to challenge me
makes me want to vomit.
Hey, Rogue!
Thanks for the power!
Now go, White Shadow Dragon!
I've got a fire in my belly.
On to the next desire.
One you will not
be able to resist.
This spell is known
as "Rest In Peace."
Call it whatever you want,
but you're still gonna lose.
Once I've ended your life,
Natsu Dragneel will be
the next one to perish.
[STING] Are you tryin'
to get me more fired up?
'Cause whether you like it or
not, that's what's happening!
Natsu, come on, just
open your eyes. Natsu!
Natsu.
This is bad.
His temperature is
continuing to drop.
If this keeps up...
No.
Wake up!
[LUCY]
Natsu!
Sting absorbs Rogue's power
and overwhelms Larcade with
a powerful combination
of White and Shadow magic.
But the enemy still unleashes
his Rest In Peace spell
in an attempt to lull
Sting into a slumber
from which he can never awake.
Can the Master of Sabertooth
find a way to combat
the irresistible waves of
desire washing over him?
Next Time: "Sting,
the White Shadow Dragon."
The combined powers form
an unbendable iron will.