[NARRATOR] It's day four
of the Grand Magic Games,
and the long-anticipated
clash of the Dragon Slayers
is finally taking
place, with two pairs
of the legendary
wizards facing off!
Fire and iron going
head to head against
the still unknown powers
of white and shadow.
Two of Fairy Tail's strongest
versus Sabertooth's
Twin Dragons.
A fight that will test
not only their strength,
but their spirits and the
bonds of friendship as well.
[NATSU] Oopsie daisy!
Huh?
Hey! Wait. What the crap?
[GAJEEL] Aaahhh!
He-heh.
I can handle the
two of you myself.
Come on! Give me all you got!
[CHAPATI] Insanity! Natsu
Dragneel has declared his own
one-on-two battle
against the Twin Dragons!
We could be witnessing history!
Are you getting' fired up?
[HAPPY] Natsu versus
the Twin Dragons!
Show 'em who's boss, Natsu!
Gajeel's gonna come back
to the fight, isn't he?
My darling Gray is
so handsome and strong!
He's also not even
fighting in this round.
C'mon, Rogue.
You got this, Sting!
Show this clown he's
messin' with the wrong guy!
[CROWD cheering]
♪
[JELLAL] Huh?
That power. I sense it again!
It's very similar to Zeref.
But still different.
They're here. Hiding
somewhere amongst the crowd.
[ULTEAR] Whatever happens,
you mustn't let them escape!
[JELLAL] I know! As much as
I'd like to stay and watch,
I have to catch them!
[STING] You think you
can take us on alone?
That's a big mistake!
I have no interest
in fighting you.
My only target is Gajeel.
You beat me, and you can
take on whoever you want.
[STING and ROGUE gasp]
[STING] Did you forget we have
control over Dragon Force?
There's nothing in the world
stronger than a dragon,
and both of us
have their power.
[yells]
I don't think that you're
all the way there yet, pal.
[growls]
Listen.
It sounds like the crowd
is getting worked up.
Prolly 'cause Fairy Tail's
kicking serious butt.
Manly style.
I know you're fascinated
by these fights.
But your main concern
should be recovering.
Focus on healing and
regaining the power you lost.
[EVERGREEN] Yes, but.
Don't worry about Natsu!
I'm sure he's okay.
Yes, he and Gajeel both.
In fact, if you look up
the word "tough"
in the dictionary,
there's probably a picture
of them right next to it.
[CARLA] They'll be fine.
Yeah, you're right!
Of course she is.
Good one, Carla!
You're the man!
As a proud woman,
I highly resent that!
[WENDY and LUCY laugh]
Oh, these kids.
[STING] This is the power
of a true Dragon Slayer!
I should know!
It's how I killed Weisslogia!
Huh. Is that so? Then I should
use the same kinda power...
that I used to fight for
my friends you laughed at!
♪
[STING] Augh!
Whoa! Look out!
Behind you!
Shadow Dragon Roar!
Fire Dragon Roar!
[grunts]
I'm not done with you!
[ROGUE] Frosch. Don't worry.
I'm not giving up now.
Bring it on.
Now give him the beatin'
he's been askin for!
I think he's having fun.
He's just grinning
away like an idiot.
Natsu's one of a kind.
[ERZA] He can increase
his own power
in response to his opponents.
He draws from it, like
an unending reservoir.
So the stronger they are,
the better he performs.
Our boy may be winning,
but the tenacity of
[MAKAROV] the other
two is remarkable.
You're right,
it's very impressive.
[NATSU] Yaaahhh!
What an amazing battle.
He's a strange one.
He seems so empty-headed.
But when he fights, his mind
moves at lightning speed.
The fire wizard's
giving off a potent parfum.
Yeah. I've never seen
anybody like him before.
[STING] Ahhh!
Wow. Nice hit.
He's doing what he does best.
So, is Gajeel
coming back or what?
I'll bet when he does,
he's not gonna
be happy about all this.
[yells]
[NATSU yells]
What the hell's
goin' on down there?
This is quite
peculiar. I've no memory
of the Dragon Force
overwhelmed in such a way.
Nor do I. Ugh!
[panting]
[LECTOR] No, Sting!
[YOUNG LECTOR] I want you to
teach me everything you know!
I just saw you fight
and I wanna be strong,
just like you are!
Oh yeah? Ya saw that and
you're not afraid of me?
I'm not afraid! I swear.
Teach me how to
be strong like you!
I'm s'posed to teach a cat?
[YOUNG LECTOR] Will ya?
Yeah, it's cool with me.
Let's get started!
Please stay strong.
[STING panting]
Now, Sting!
Yeah!
[JUVIA] Can you feel it?
Their magic power seems to
have changed yet again.
It's definitely changed.
Because they've started
to merge together.
[LECTOR] I never got
strong like I wanted to.
But I've always loved
watching you in action.
You're awesome!
They're attempting
a Unison Raid!
The power they each held
separately is now one.
It can prove to be quite
a devastating attack.
[MAVIS] However...
Natsu! Out of the way!
Come on. You can do it, Rogue.
They can pull it off!
[LECTOR] Because no one's
ever gonna take Sting down!
[MAVIS] There are some
walls that power alone
will never break through.
Oh no.
Holy cow. What's going on?
Looks like a Unison Raid.
It's what you might
call fusion magic.
[YAJIMA] It's generally
considered to be such an
advanced technique that
you could spend your
entire life training
and never master it.
[MINERVA] The ultimate power
of our Twin Dragons. But...
[BOTH] Holy Shadow
Dragon Flash Fang!
He's not moving!
[PANTHERLILY] Does he
think he can block it?
[HAPPY] Hey, Natsu.
Yeah, what's up?
Is something wrong, buddy?
[GAJEEL] You two can have your
little moment. I'm goin' in.
[HAPPY] Nothing's wrong.
Oh, cool. Well, it's show time!
Hold on. I'm not
gonna say anything.
Do you know what
I mean by that?
Hm.
[NATSU] Yeah.
I hear ya, Partner.
[distant rumbling]
[CHAPATI] The energy is
electric here in Domus Flau!
We may be seeing
history in the making!
Can Fairy Tail take
back Sabertooth's title
as Fiore's mightiest?
Four dragons are squaring
off in a battle so intense,
it's crashed through the floor!
[YAJIMA] One seems to
be missing in action.
[CHAPATI] Right you are,
which means Fairy Tail's
Natsu Dragneel has to win
the match all by himself!
It's gotten rather quiet.
Kinda. But there's a
weird tension in the air.
[CARLA]
Can you sense it, child?
[WENDY] Yeah.
I wonder what it is.
[NATSU] Hey. Are ya
feelin' any better?
[LUCY] I'm getting there.
Is your match about to start?
[NATSU] Yep. And I'm
gonna win it for sure.
[LUCY] Natsu.
Huh?
I believe in you.
And I always have,
from the moment
I joined the guild.
Thanks! That means a lot to me.
[EVERGREEN] Please, I think your
bandages are just too tight!
[ELFMAN] You're just jealous
'cause you can't feel it!
[PORLYUSICA] Would you stop the
"old married couple" routine?
[EVERGREEN and ELFMAN]
We're not a couple!
I will always be
watching over you.
No matter what happens. Right?
[CARLA and WENDY giggle]
[PORLYUSICA]
You've really done it.
You've taken this group
of misfits and made them
into a strong and
loving family. Bravo.
[MAVIS] There are some
walls that power alone
will never break through.
However...
it is possible
to get beyond them.
[BOTH] Holy Shadow
Dragon Flash Fang!
[MAVIS] If you
harness your feelings...
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
[NATSU] Flame Lotus
Exploding Flame Blade!
[CHAPATI] Whoa momma!
The fighters have unleashed
major techniques and
the clash is sending
shockwaves all
throughout the arena!
It seems to have had an
effect on the lacrima-trons!
Just some technical
difficulties, folks.
We should be back up soon!
I don't sense
any magic power.
I think the fight
might be over, you guys.
[CHAPATI] All right!
Ladies and gentlemen,
looks like we are
back in business!
Sorry for the delay, but who
could have seen that coming?
[ROGUE groans]
Natsu... Dragneel...
Your power... knows no bounds.
[STING]
Sorry, Lector. I failed.
He's... too strong.
[CHAPATI] Unbelievable.
The last man standing
is Fairy Tail's Natsu Dragneel!
[MAVIS] A guild is a place where
those feelings are nurtured.
--[bell dinging]
--[NATSU] Yeah!
[CROWD cheers]
[CHAPATI] Let's hear it for
Natsu, who singlehandedly
took down Sabertooth's
Twin Dragons!
[BOTH laughing]
[CHAPATI] It's a huge
win for Fairy Tail!
They've moved into first place!
What an exciting
way to end day four
of the Grand Magic Games!
We're giving the fighters
a day to recuperate,
and then it's on to
the thrilling conclusion!
It's all culminating
in one ultimate match!
A game that puts
every team member
on the field to duke it
out in a battle royale!
Only one guild
gets the title, folks!
So... you won't
want to miss it!
[CROWD cheering]
I just knew the fairies
would end up on top!
There's no doubt about it.
They're a wild bunch!
Thanks to this
big turn-around,
we're gonna have to
beat them instead.
Heh. Bring it!
[GUILDS] Fairy Tail
is goin' down!
Watch out, Gray.
I'm coming!
My target...
is the would-be-heir, Laxus.
Titania.
Let's find Gajeel.
[ICHIYA] Your parfum is
irresistible... Natsu.
[LECTOR crying]
It'll be okay.
[crying]
I can't believe they
both got their butts
handed to 'em by one guy.
[RUFUS chuckles]
It was fascinating to behold.
I've fully committed
it to memory.
Heh. I'm gonna have a
lotta fun holdin' this
over their heads for a while.
[MINERVA] Perhaps you will.
Of course, that's assuming
they have that long.
This guy's about
to explode over here!
[MALE 175B] That's
Sabertooth's master!
[MINERVA] So your power
comes from feelings, does it?
[STING] Fine, whatever.
I didn't need this win,
so I'll just let you guys have
it. Sabertooth's just gonna
keep rackin' up
the points after this.
In the end, one
measly little point
isn't gonna change the outcome.
One point is nothin'
to scoff at, kid.
[GAJEEL] Don't you forget that!
[STING grunts]
[NATSU] Let's do
it again sometime!
[ROGUE] A complete and
utter loss. I wonder...
could Gajeel be as
strong a fighter as Natsu?
[ROGUE] If that's true,
how could I have
ever been so arrogant?
Way to go, pal!
Let's go tell Lucy that
Fairy Tail is back on top!
That was pretty
freakin' awesome, man!
Thanks, dude! I had fun!
What you did today
deserves genuine praise!
You're really
something else, Natsu.
Ah, ya think?
Yeah.
That hurt!
I applaud your victory.
But do you know what
happened to your partner?
Oh, ya mean Gajeel?
Yeah, that jerk took off
in the middle of the fight.
Did he just forget that he
was on my team all of a sudden?
More like, you just forgot
what you did to your teammate.
That's classic Natsu!
Be sure to remember that
tomorrow is a day of rest.
And then it's on
to the final round.
I can't wait for that.
We're gonna be number
one in Fiore again!
And when that's done!
I'll fight both you turkeys
for the number one
spot in the guild!
I'll be ready.
Let's just get past these
games first, okay guys?
[ELFMAN and WENDY chuckle]
It's good to see you.
You're not gonna
ask how it went?
I don't need to. I told
you I believed in you,
since the very beginning.
Hm. But this still ain't over.
We're just gettin' started.
We still gotta win this
thing! Well, don't we?
Of course, child. We've
come this far after all.
Can ya believe we started off
at the bottom of the barrel?
The audience had
the gall to boo us.
We suffered defeat and
humiliation along the way.
But now we can
practically taste victory!
Natsu? Remember what you said?
It was right after I lost
my fight against Flare.
You told me that zero
points was a great place
to start an epic comeback.
That's right! We're
climbing back to the top!
Fairy Tail wizards never back
down and we're not startin' now!
[MAKAROV] Let's win
the thirty million Jewel!
[ALL] That's not why we're here!
First place! Ya with me?
[ALL] Yeah!
[LUCY] So much has happened
since I first joined this guild.
So many tears, so many laughs.
So many special
moments I got to share
with people that
mean the world to me.
I couldn't be more
proud to call myself
a member of Fairy Tail!
[giggles]
[GAJEEL] Damn you, Salamander.
If you lived through that fight,
I'm gonna kill you for this.
Where the hell
am I, anyway?
Still under the coliseum?
Hm?
Whoa. I don't believe it.
[GAJEEL] Is this some
kinda dragon graveyard?
[ULTEAR]
Jellal. What's going on?
[MELDY] Oh no,
did they get away again?
[JELLAL] No.
I'm still tailing them.
I'm waiting for the
opportunity to make my move.
[ULTEAR and MELDY] Understood.
[JELLAL] I'm not letting
you out of my sight.
I need to find out
why you remind me
so much of Zeref. Who are you?
[YUKINO] So Natsu's done it.
He's defeated Sabertooth
all by himself.
[IRIKI] You must feel a bit
conflicted, Sergeant Yukino.
[YUKINO] No. My attachments to
that guild have been severed.
[YUKINO] I'm fine.
What's difficult is
getting used to being
called "Sergeant."
I understand completely, ma'am.
But your involvement with
Eclipse requires a rank.
It's a military
project, after all.
You'll get used
to it soon enough.
This is an
important undertaking.
[YUKINO] I am prepared
to do whatever may be
required of me to ensure the
success of this operation.
And I'm very grateful
to Arcadios...
for extending his invitation.
Wait. I suppose I should
call him "Colonel" instead.
Don't worry about it.
I usually just call
him "sir" myself.
[IRIKI] Some of his oldest
friends get away with "Dio."
Is that so?
[YUKINO] He doesn't
seem to have many friends.
[YUKINO] It's bizarre.
He's trying to save the world,
but nobody knows about it.
[gasps]
What's up? Are you okay?
Yes.
[CARLA] It's that
strange premonition again.
Mercurius crashing down.
[LEVY] Did you hear? We won!
[LUCY] Hey guys!
Are you two starting
to feel any better?
I brought snacks,
if you're hungry!
If we can keep
our spirits up,
we're gonna win
this thing after all!
Oh yeah! There's no way Team
Fairy Tail is losing now!
That's right! Especially
after seeing that fight today!
We are on a real hot streak,
and there's
just one more to go!
You wouldn't know where
Gajeel went, would ya?
Haven't seen him
since before the fight.
[LUCY] What? Ya mean
he's still not back yet?
[ELFMAN] He's probably stuffin'
his face with iron somewhere.
[LUCY] He'll be back
before too long.
[WENDY] Sure he will!
Hmmm...
[LEVY] It was nice. Everyone was
positive that we were winning.
Then the fight on that
final day was so intense.
Do you remember it, Lucy?
[LEVY] That happiness
was such a stark contrast
to what was to come.
On that fateful day...
July seventh.
When everything we'd
hoped for turned to ash.
[LEVY] First they died.
Then we lost.
We loved them so much. But...
[LEVY] I can barely even
write this. Please, Lucy.
I can't take it anymore.
I just want someone to help me.
[JELLAL] Stop right there!
Reveal your identity.
I have already revealed mine.
[JELLAL] A woman?
No way!
[LUCY, HAPPY, and NATSU]
Thanks, everybody!
[NATSU] We'll catch
you later, okay?