[NATSU moans]
♪
This is torture.
Come on.
Make it stop.
Hold those guts in for
two hours and then that's it.
We're done!
[CARLA] Can he be
any more pathetic?
But that's so long.
Maybe you should put
another Troia spell
on the poor guy.
With all this sweating,
crying, and throwing up,
I'm afraid that
he's gonna melt away.
Yeah, you're right.
Troia!
Poor Natsu!
He--
Eewww!
[HAPPY] True Scoundrels--
The Butt Jiggle Gang!
Ugh. I'm dying.
You gotta save me. Please.
I don't know
why it didn't work.
I'll try to do it again.
Troia!
I feel so funky.
[WENDY] Troia!
Troia!!
Troia!!!
Why won't it fix me?
I don't know!
That's really weird; it
normally perks him right up.
Not this time.
I'm fairly certain
that I know why it failed.
This spell has been used
on him over and over again
on several long journeys.
So much so that it's
ceased to work at all!
No.
Like I'm immune?
Whoa.
That can
actually happen?
Well, it would certainly
appear it can.
I'm surprised it's
lasted for this long,
but he is a bit
slow on the uptake.
You'll have
to grin and bear it.
Sorry pal, but we'll be
there in a couple of hours.
I'm sorry.
Two more hours?
I'm gonna run out of puke.
[NATSU pukes]
[NARRATOR] Our nauseous hero
and his friends have taken
a job providing security
for a very precious cargo.
Their client is an
extremely rich man
who is attempting to send a
large amount of gold bullion
to one of his
associates by train.
They're to escort
this traveling mint
on a six-hour trip
across the countryside,
and ensure its safe passage.
Four hours have passed,
and besides
the motion sickness,
it's been a peaceful journey.
But unbeknownst
to Natsu and company,
there is an evil
presence on the train.
A silent, but deadly force,
waiting to erupt.
[suffocated screams]
[evil laughs]
[MAN] All right!
Let's blow!
[LACKEYS] Yeah!
Who moves in like a fog
and steals all the booty?
[ALL] The
Butt Jiggle Gang!
[farts]
[BUTT BOSS]
Sound off, lackey A!
[BUTT LACKEY A] Boom!
[BUTT BOSS] Sound off,
lackey B!
[BUTT LACKEY B] Boom!
Okay!
[continuous farting]
Operation "Steal the
Entire Freight Car Carrying
the Gold Bullion and Scram"
blasting off now!
[BUTT LACKEYS] Bombs away!
[BUTT BOSS] That there
is a rolling gold mine.
[BUTT LACKEY A] We're
gonna be so stinkin' rich!
[BUTT BOSS] Yeah, no crap.
I can practically
smell the good life!
Who is that,
and what is he doing here?
The plan hinges
on the coast being clear!
So do we need to
change the plan?
What are we gonna
do about him?
Relax boys.
The plan to the get
the gold is still airtight.
This is just a hiccup.
We can still
squeak out a win.
[farts]
[BUTT BOSS] Listen up!
I'll simply distract
the little stinker.
while you two sneak
inside the freight car.
[BUTT LACKEYS] Solid!
Hey, buddy,
you feelin' okay?
[BUTT LACKEY A] Butting in...
Butting in...
You look a little green.
Traveling not
agreeing with you?
Oh yeah.
Always makes me sick.
Sucks.
Thanks for asking, though.
Ya know?
I think I'm actually startin' to
feel a little bit better now.
You're a real nice guy.
I'm a nice guy?
Yeah, totally.
Much nicer than my
so-called 'friends' in there,
who took on this job knowing
that I'd be blowing chunks
the entire trip.
Whaddaya mean?
What kind of 'job' are
you and your friends on?
Guard duty.
For the cargo in that
freight car there.
Oh?
And they're
inside right now?
[BUTT LACKEY A] We should be
able to get a peek through here.
[BUTT LACKEY B]
Open the window.
[BUTT LACKEY A]
I'll crack it a bit.
It's not your fault
that he got too used
to the spell, Wendy.
[CARLA] Don't bother
trying to cheer her up;
she'll be sulking for a while
no matter what you say.
Besides, Natsu knew
exactly what he was in for.
He gets sick, so he should
never have taken the job.
Yeah, you're right.
It was dumb, but I think he
just wanted something to do.
It's not him.
If I can't use my magic
when it's needed the most.
I'm a complete
failure of a wizard.
You're an awesome wizard.
Don't be silly!
[BUTT LACKEYS]
Whoa, they're wizards?
[BUTT BOSS] That
really does stink, bub.
When you're trying to
work together as a group,
you hope things will come out
smoothly, and you definitely
don't want any rumblings
from those beneath you.
That's just how I feel!
Thank you!
That's it.
Toss those cookies, pal
[BUTT LACKEYS] Boss.
Are you trying to make
me soil my bodysuit?
There are people
inside the freight car.
I know that.
Somebody hired them
to guard the cargo.
From the way they
were talkin',
it sounds like
they're wizards.
They all got this
mark on 'em, too.
That must mean
they're affiliated
with a guild, huh?
It's gonna make things
a bit more difficult.
[NATSU] Well.
I'm all outta cookies to toss.
There's more of ya.
[BUTT BOSS] Yeah, these two
are just my traveling buddies.
They heard you weren't
feeling very good.
They're real nice guys,
just like me.
We could never think
about turning our backs
on a stranger in need.
For real?
There should be
more people like you!
Hey, it's okay.
You'll get your second
wind real soon, I'm sure.
[knock on door]
[LUCY] Natsu?
Ya had enough
fresh air?
[HAPPY] Maybe he's
feeling better now.
[CARLA] He's not
the brightest,
so perhaps it took a while
for the spell to effect him.
[WENDY] You okay?
Come on in.
Hi there!
[BUTT LACKEYS]
So nice to meet you!
[WENDY] Ohhhh.
I...
Uhhhh...
[BUTT BOSS] Please,
excuse us for just a moment.
Hold it right there!
This freight car is for
authorized personnel only.
Oh, I see.
But we found this poor
young man passed out
in front of the doorway.
Oh no!
He passed out?
[CARLA] His condition is far
more serious than we thought.
[LUCY] Man,
this stinks.
Poor Natsu.
[HAPPY] Come
on, buddy.
Talk to us!
[evil chuckle]
[HAPPY] What the-?
[BUTT BOSS] No funny stuff!
Make one move and
the little girl gets it.
That was an awesome
threat, boss!
Like a true
scoundrel!
What's goin' on here?
Don't tell me you
guys are trying to get
your grubby hands
on this cargo!
Of course we are!
And we ain't
afraid of no wizards!
'Cause we're as
rotten as they come!
[continuous farts]
[ALL] They call us
The Butt Jiggle Gang!
[LUCY] Seriously?
[CARLA] Disgusting.
[HAPPY] Natsu's really
not lookin' so good.
Shut your pie-holes!
Now boys!
Let's power up!
[BUTT LACKEYS] Yeah!
[BUTT JIGGLE GANG chants] Booty
Booty Booty Booty Booty Booty...
What the heck
are you doing?
Is this some kind of joke?
I'm afraid of
the punch line.
[HAPPY] I think
I'm gonna be sick, too.
Listen up!
The contents of this car
are now the property
of the Butt Jiggle Gang.
And you kids need
to blast on outta here!
Are you freaking
kidding me?
We won't leave cause you're
shaking your butts at us!
You're gonna be eating
your words, girlie.
I'm scared, Lucy!
Yeah.
It'll be okay, Wendy.
These goons wouldn't
dare hurt you!
That's right,
I bet they're just
a bunch of old windbags!
I'm warnin' ya.
you'd better blow,
or we're gonna!
[BUTT LACKEY A] Well?
[BUTT LACKEY B] Well?
[BUTT BOSS] Welly welly well?
[ALL] Well?!
Full of beans now!
Ready?
Fire the colon cannon!
[BUTT LACKEY A]
Gas butt.
[BUTT LACKEY B]
Triple.
[BUTT BOSS] Ecstasy!
[explosive fart]
[HAPPY] Pee yew!
[CARLA] Yucky!
Guys, no!
The stink's in my nose.
and it's sticking
to my clothing!
I think it even
burned my skin!
Help me!
[HAPPY] Not like this!
[CARLA] So undignified!
Thanks, you really
saved my life!
It's burning
my nose!
That foul odor is
sapping my strength!
I can't go on.
Me neither!
[LUCY] No!
Please!
Don't give up!
We're gonna die!
[WENDY] Wait,
where is everyone?
Plue!
I'm so happy you're safe.
Natsu!
Please wake up!
Hello?
Mister?
What in
the hell is that?
Plue.
He's a Celestial
Spirit.
So cute!
I know I'm as bad as they come,
but somethin' about him
just melts my evil heart.
Uhhhh.
[BUTT BOSS]
Alright, ya bums!
Move your rumps!
Get up!
[BUTT LACKEY B]
This place stinks.
Hey, check it out!
A Celestial Spirit!
Have you ever
seen such a thing?
[BUTT LACKEYS] Oh my god!
[BUTT LACKEY A]
He's adorable.
[BUTT LACKEY B]
He makes me feel funny.
Cutie patootie!
Um...
excuse me.
Whoops!
Truly evil,
wicked scoundrels like us
should never lose our focus!
Now drop to your
bellies and then
give me twenty three!
Whadda we gotta
do that for, boss?
And why such a
random number?
Because the boss says
so, that's why!
[BUTT LACKEYS]
1.
2.
3--
[WENDY] I hope the
others are okay,
but now it's up to me
to protect the gold.
So when they're done,
what are you
planning to do next?
Are you kidding me?
We're gonna take this loot
and break like the wind.
Unless you can stop
us by yourself,
ya little squirt.
Plue's here, too!
That just means
there's gonna be one more
hostage around for us to grab.
So you try anything
sneaky and your friend here
is gonna be neck
deep in a brown cloud.
[BUTT LACKEY A] Okay boss.
[BUTT LACKEY B] We did
just what you asked us to.
Good 'cause we
got work to do.
B!
You know what this calls for?
Yup!
[BUTT LACKEY B]
♪ Dun da da duhhh ♪
Dynamite?
Yeah!
That's called
pinching it off!
Oh no!
The freight car!
Ha!
It's ours now!
It's been claimed as property
of the Butt Jiggle Gang!
[BUTT LACKEYS]
Smell ya later!
Ready the thrusters!
Unleash the Triple Gas Butt
Ecstasy Second Salvo!
Fire!
[BUTT JIGGLE GANG] Whoopee!!!
[HAPPY] What's
goin on up there?
[echoing farts]
Alright.
Let's go after 'em!
[CARLA] Well, my nose
has recovered, so I'm ready!
In your face!
Kiss it, wizards!
Your guild ain't got nothin'
on the Butt Jiggle Gang!
You may
have done this.
but the car can't
keep going forever.
Can the three of you
just keep on tooting
your way down the tracks?
Plus, if you do get where
you want to go, then what?
There's a lot of gold.
Do you know how
you're gonna carry it away?
[WENDY] Are you serious?
I would think that an expert
gang of thieves would've thought
that far ahead.
The car ain't movin'
anymore, boss!
How are we gonna
make it go again?
[evil laugh]
A true scoundrel
always has a plan,
so listen to me!
Not only does
our gang have brain power.
We've got brawn power, too!
Good thinkin', boss!
We'll do it
the old fashioned way.
roll up our sleeves,
flex our muscles,
and put our backs into it!
[BUTT LACKEYS]
No! Boss!
Mister, are you okay?
Do I look like
I'm doing okay?
I can help you!
You can?
Yes, sir.
I specialize in healing magic.
I'm not sure, but I think that
I can make you feel better.
Is it
working, boss?
Oh wow!
It's like the pain is just
floating right out of me.
That's amazing!
This little girl
is amazing!
Thanks for
your help, missy.
Worked like a charm.
You're welcome.
So, tell me.
If your magic
is that powerful.
Why don't you cast a healing
spell on your sick friend
down there?
[WENDY] I do have a spell
especially for motion sickness.
But for some
reason it just doesn't
work on him anymore.
It's my fault.
If I was a better wizard I
could use a more powerful spell
that could help him.
Don't cry.
I know you'll
get better someday.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Lucky for me, Fairy Tail
is full of nice people
that wanna help me grow.
And I'll always
be grateful that I was able
to find them when I did.
[BUTT LACKEYS] So sweet!
Thanks for
listening to me.
You guys seem like
super nice people, too.
Slow down.
Let's try to not get
carried away here, kid.
We are not nice guys.
We are true scoundrels
from the bowels of society.
That means we are
only in it for ourselves.
So, you never actually
answered my question...
How're you gonna get
the gold outta here?
Yeah boss, that's
a lotta booty
to be carryin' around.
How are we gonna pull
this thing off, boss?
I get it, lackeys!
Let's huddle up!
[BUTT BOSS] Is anyone
else's butt getting chaffed--?
[WENDY] I wish
Natsu was better.
I wonder what he'd do
if he were awake right now.
Or Lucy, what would she do?
[WENDY] That's it!
Umm,
Sorry to butt in...
What is it?
[BUTT LACKEY A] You wanna
give me a heart attack?
You guys came here
because you wanted to steal
the gold really bad,
didn't you?
I think I may have
a better idea.
How about I talk
to the client and ask if
he'll share some
of it with you?
[BUTT LACKEY B] You think he'd
actually go for that plan?
But I do have one
condition for you.
You gotta promise you'll
never do anything bad again.
Stop pulling
my leg, little girl.
I guess you can just forget
about getting any gold.
[BUTT LACKEYS] Aw, man!
You guys promise
to be good and I promise
I'll move the freight car.
But how are you
gonna do that?
[WENDY] Well, it's
a lot like the way
you guys did it earlier,
but a little different.
You can do a Gas
Butt Triple Ecstasy
all by yourself?
No!
That's not what I meant!
So,
I guess you got
a deal, squirt.
Lackeys...
huddle up.
[BUTT LACKEYS] Right!
Listen.
We'll pretend to go along
with her goody two-shoes plan,
but truly rotten scoundrels
like us would never
be satisfied if we didn't
take all of the booty.
We get her guard
down a bit and then
we take every last
brick of gold.
Real fiendish plan.
You definitely
got the brains
of a true scoundrel,
that's for sure.
[BUTT BOSS] Alright ya little
stinker, let's see what ya got!
How is she gonna do this
without the gas butt?
No clue.
She's a puny little squeaker,
but she's also part of
some kinda
wizard guild.
Maybe she's got some
crazy magical power.
The only thing
we can do is wait
to see what happens.
Okay, here I go.
Sky Dragon
Roar!
[BUTT LACKEY A] Holy!
[BUTT LACKEY B] That's crazy!
Sky Dragon magic!
That means Wendy!
Come on!
Let's hurry!
So whaddya think?
This should probably make up
for quite a bit of the time
that we lost.
Wow, you're incredible.
Was that Dragon Slayer magic?
Oh...
yeah.
[ALL] Will you let us
call you Little Lady Boss?
I've never met anyone
so incredibly powerful.
We would be honored--
no, thrilled--
if you'd agree
to be our goddess!
Please say yes.
And you'll get to wear your
own tiny Butt Jiggle Bodysuit!
Say yes, and
we'll follow you
to the ends of the Earth!
I don't know!
It seems like a whole
lotta responsibility!
Lackeys!
Huddle!
Are you serious about
all this stuff, boss?
Of course I am.
Extremely.
It's perfect.
[BUTT BOSS] If we had someone
this powerful on our side
we would be unstoppable.
There's nothing we couldn't do.
Which also means there's
nothing we couldn't steal.
[BUTT LACKEY B]
Good thinkin', boss!
[WENDY] What do I do now?
I guess I have to pretend
to be part of their gang
for a little while.
I have to
try to be strong!
The reputation of the Fairy
Tail guild is in my hands.
[BUTT BOSS] So, for the next
part of the plan we gotta--
[WENDY] Um,
excuse me.
[BUTT LACKEY A]
She's precious!
I'm so happy!
This is the greatest thing the
Butt Jiggle Gang has ever done!
So does this mean
you're gonna be our goddess?
[WENDY] Yeah.
This calls for
a special occasion pose!
What's our name?
[ALL] The Butt Jiggle Gang!
We quit movin', you guys!
[BUTT BOSS] Alright goddess,
do your thing!
[WENDY] Okay!
Sky Dragon--
[LUCY] Stop right there!
[BUTT JIGGLE GANG] What the--??
Natsu's still inside!
Cool!
[HAPPY] You goin'
scuba diving?
Wendy?
Would you care
to explain yourself?
Oh.
I'm their...
goddess!
Natsu!
Get up buddy, you gotta
snap out it of it!
[HAPPY] The train's stopped.
Do you feel better now?
Yeah.
The world's not
spinning anymore.
Wendy needs your help!
Come on!
She does?
[LUCY] Now spill it!
What did you do
to our friend?
[CARLA] If you hurt
that little girl!
I will go straight
for your throats!
I'm beggin' ya goddess,
you're the only one
who can save our butts!
Well,
whatever you do,
don't fight 'em.
Lackeys...
huddle up!
[BUTT JIGGLE GANG] Right!
Is she in
their gang now?
I have absolutely no idea
what the heck's happening here.
Or why they're
calling her "goddess."
Listen.
Maybe the plan needs to be to
stop being 'true scoundrels'.
Maybe you guys should try
bein' wizards instead.
Fairy Tail has some
correspondence classes
you could take.
I'll even put in a good word
for you if you're interested.
Do you mean it?
You care about
us bums that much?
These feelings are
all so new to me.
I've never even thought
about my future.
Little lady boss,
you're the nicest person
we've ever met!
[LUCY] This is
starting to get weird.
[CARLA] Wendy can get anyone
to like her even undesirables
like these.
It's her gift,
I suppose.
[LUCY] Yeah,
some gift.
[NATSU] Alright, you turds!
Natsu!
I explained to him
what's going on!
Wendy,
these bad guys are taking
you hostage, aren't they?
No, it's not really
like that, Happy!
[NATSU] You guys were just
pretending to be nice to me
because you wanted to
steal from my client?
Getting tricked
like that makes me angry!
No!
Fire Dragon...
Hold on, Natsu!
They're changing their ways!
[NATSU] Iron fist!
[LUCY] Whoa.
[CARLA] Just
look at them fly.
[WENDY] Those poor guys.
I don't think they were
anywhere near as bad
as they pretended to be.
[CLIENT] Just how long were
you planning to make me wait?
Sorry, but we ran into
some trouble along the way.
Ugh!
Why does my body hate me?
We're on solid
ground again, ya know?
Still,
I'll be halving your pay.
A bit harsh.
Hey, Wendy.
you need to work
your magic on this guy.
Melt his heart and
get him on our side.
Those big butt bad guys
cost us big bucks.
We ain't goin' out
with a whimper!
The Butt Jiggle Gang's
not done yet.
We won't be
silenced that easy!
Yeah.
We're coming back
loud and strong!
And we'll be right
behind ya, boss man!
Ready?
Gas Butt Triple Ecstasy!
We'll return with a bang,
as true scoundrels!
Right lackeys?
[BUTT JIGGLE GANG] They ain't
heard the last of us!
♪
[HAPPY laughs]
[NATSU] I got you now,
Dark Lord Happy!
Take this, Fire Dragon Roar!
[HAPPY] You missed
me Salamander!
I'm over here!
[NATSU] Hey!
You've got
invisibility magic?
That's so not fair!
C'mon, fight me for real!
[HAPPY, laughing]
Now, I'm over here!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
The Terror of Invisible Lucy!
You're not so good
at this vanishing act.
[HAPPY] I think it's because
I want to be in the
spotlight too much.
[NATSU] Yeah, you do strike me
as kinda desperate for fame.