- Narrator:
BACK IN EARTH LAND,
ON THE OUTSKIRTS
OF THE TOWN OF MAGNOLIA...
- ( screams )
( groaning )
- ( chuckles )
WE'RE BACK, EVERYBODY!
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTASY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP WITH
A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ( all gasping )
- ( bell rings )
- ( Natsu laughs )
EVERYTHING'S BACK TO NORMAL!
- Lucy: THERE'S MAGNOLIA!
- Happy: WE DID IT!
- Erza: WAIT.
LET'S NOT GET
AHEAD OF OURSELVES.
WE SHOULDN'T CELEBRATE
UNTIL WE KNOW EVERYBODY'S OKAY.
- THEY'RE JUST FINE.
WE GOT HERE A WHILE AGO,
SO WE WENT AND
CHECKED ON 'EM FOR YOU.
- WE DECIDED TO FLY
THROUGH TOWN REAL QUICK.
- YOUR FRIENDS AND EVERYONE
IN TOWN ARE DOING GREAT.
- WHEN WE TALKED TO THEM,
THEY DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THEY'D BEEN TURNED
INTO A LACRIMA.
- EARTH LAND IS TOTALLY AWESOME,
YOU GUYS.
IT'S GOT TONS
OF MAGIC POWER.
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
IT'S NOT RIGHT!
- ( cheering )
- Carla: THE EXCEEDS DON'T
BELONG IN EARTH LAND!
- ( Happy speaking )
- WE CANNOT ALLOW THEM
TO STAY HERE.
THEY'RE FAR TOO DANGEROUS.
THEY SHOULD
RETURN TO EDOLAS.
- BE NICE.
- THEIR HOMELAND'S GONE
SO THEY HAVE NOWHERE TO GO.
I THINK THAT WE SHOULD
FORGIVE THEM.
- NEVER!
- WE APOLOGIZE
FOR THROWING ROCKS
AT YOU, LADY.
- WE'RE REALLY SORRY.
- WE HAVE
NO PLACE TO GO NOW
THAT EXTALIA'S
BEEN DESTROYED.
- WE PROMISE THAT
WE'LL BE NICER TO YOU, NOW.
- PLEASE SAY YOU'LL FORGIVE US.
- THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU KIDS!
IT'S HER! I'M ANGRY
BECAUSE EXTALIA'S QUEEN
AND HER LACKEYS
SENT ME TO EARTH LAND
ON A MISSION TO KILL
THE DRAGON SLAYERS.
- I KNOW!
THE QUEEN ORDERED US
TO GIVE UP ALL OUR EGGS.
HOW CAN SHE BE
SO HEARTLESS?!
GAH!
- CALM DOWN, DEAR.
- HEY THERE, MISTER.
- YEAH, NO JOKE.
SHE NEVER EVEN
TOLD US WHY, DID SHE?
- I CAN ASSURE YOU
THAT SHE HAD
A MOST HONORABLE
REASON TO DO SO.
- I REMEMBER
THE MOMENT VIVIDLY.
IT WAS SIX YEARS AGO.
- Martam:
AS I MENTIONED BEFORE,
QUEEN CHAGOT
HAS THE ABILITY
TO GLIMPSE INTO THE FUTURE.
IT IS BOTH A GIFT
AND A CURSE.
ONE DAY...
- ( gasps )
- Mejeer:
EXTALIA WILL FALL?
- I HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT
IF THAT'S QUEEN CHAGOT'S VISION,
I'M AFRAID IT'S BOUND
TO HAPPEN SOONER OR LATER.
- THEN WE HAVE TO
PROTECT OURSELVES.
BUT WHO WOULD
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- WHO ELSE COULD IT BE
BUT THE HUMANS?
- Present-day Martam:
WE NOW REALIZE THAT EXTALIA
WAS BOUND TO FALL
THROUGH NATURAL MEANS
DUE TO THE EXHAUSTION
OF MAGIC POWER.
HOWEVER, AT THE TIME,
WE BELIEVED OUR HOMELAND
WOULD BE DESTROYED
BY THE HUMANS.
- WHAT SHALL WE DO,
YOUR MAJESTY?
- Chagot: WE CANNOT WIN A WAR
AGAINST THE HUMANS.
- ( all sigh )
- WE'VE NO CHOICE.
SAVE THE CHILDREN.
- SAVE THEM?!
- YOU DON'T MEAN--
- ( gasps )
- WHAT THE--
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S A WAY DIFFERENT STORY
THAN THE ONE
WE WERE TOLD.
YOU AREN'T LYING TO US,
ARE YOU?
- NO, YOUNG MAN.
- TO PREVENT PANIC AMONG
THE EXTALIANS,
WE CARRIED OUT OUR PLAN
WITHOUT THEIR KNOWLEDGE.
- THE QUEEN THEN ISSUED
A FALSE PROCLAMATION.
IT WAS MERELY A COVER-UP
FOR OUR PLAN.
- THIS OPERATION
IS TO PROTECT YOU.
THESE MONSTERS,
THE DRAGON SLAYERS
MUST BE ELIMINATED.
PLEASE, I ASK FOR
YOUR UNDERSTANDING
AT THIS DIFFICULT TIME.
- Mejeer:
WE FELT HORRIBLE ABOUT
MAKING THE QUEEN
LIE TO YOU LIKE THAT.
- Muganto:
YES, BUT WE HAD NO CHOICE.
- Mysdroy: WE SIMPLY
COULD NOT GO PUBLIC
WITH THE KNOWLEDGE
THAT OUR BELOVED EXTALIA
MIGHT COME CRASHING
TO THE GROUND.
- Martam: DESPITE
WHAT YOU'VE HEARD,
I ASSURE YOU THAT
WE HAVE NO ILL-WILL
TOWARDS THE DRAGON SLAYERS
WHATSOEVER.
- Wendy: DON'T WORRY.
WE KNOW.
YOU JUST NEEDED
SOMETHING TO GO ALONG
WITH THE STORY
YOU TOLD THEM.
- YOU KNEW EVERYONE WOULD PANIC
IF THE TRUTH GOT OUT
SO YOU HAD TO MAKE UP
SOMETHING ELSE TO TELL THEM.
- WE GET IT.
- Chagot: WE MADE USE
OF THE HUMANS' ANIMA
TO SUCCESSFULLY CARRY OUT
OUR OPERATION.
HOWEVER...
SOMETHING COMPLETELY
UNEXPECTED HAPPENED
WITH ONE OF THE EGGS.
WE HAD NO IDEA
THAT YOU, CARLA,
POSSESSED AN
INCREDIBLE POWER.
- ME?
- YES, AS IT TURNS OUT,
YOU POSSESS THE SAME
PROPHETIC POWERS THAT I DO.
- ( gasps )
- UNFORTUNATELY,
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
CONSCIOUS CONTROL OVER IT.
AND AS A RESULT, IT CLOUDED
AND CONFUSED YOUR MEMORY.
OF THE 100 EXCEEDS
THAT WE SENT AWAY,
ONLY YOU HAD THIS GIFT.
I SUSPECT
THAT YOU BEGAN TO SEE
SCATTERED FRAGMENTS
OF EDOLAS'S FUTURE.
- Young Carla:
WE ARE DOING THIS
FOR THE GOOD
OF OUR KINGDOM.
MAGIC POWER WILL COMPLETELY
VANISH FROM OUR WORLD.
WE ARE SENDING OUR CHILDREN
TO ERADICATE THE MONSTROUS
DRAGON SLAYERS.
IT IS OUR MISSION.
( gasps )
- Chagot:
YOUR GIFT
CAUSED YOU TO MISTAKE
THAT INFORMATION
AS YOUR PERSONAL MISSION.
- I WAS WRONG.
- Happy: WAIT,
DOES THAT MEAN...
- Chagot: THE TWO OF YOU
WERE NEVER GIVEN A MISSION.
IT WAS JUST YOUR WAY
OF TRYING TO MAKE SENSE
OF ALL THE STRANGE THOUGHTS
AND IMAGES IN YOUR HEAD.
YOU WERE SENT HERE
BECAUSE WE WANTED
TO PROTECT
THE NEXT GENERATION.
NOTHING MORE.
- Carla: SO THOSE
WERE ALL PROPHESIES?
- FOR WHATEVER REASON,
WE THOUGHT YOU'D BE BETTER OFF
IF WE HID YOUR
PROPHETIC POWERS FROM YOU.
THEREFORE, WE HAD NO CHOICE,
BUT TO MAKE IT SEEM
AS THOUGH WE WERE
CONTROLLING YOU.
WE BEG YOUR FORGIVENESS.
- AT THE TIME,
WE HONESTLY THOUGHT
THAT WAS THE ONLY WAY
WE COULD EMBELLISH
THE QUEEN'S ILLUSTRIOUSNESS.
HOWEVER, NOW,
WE DEEPLY REGRET IT.
- THE SHOW OF FALSE BRAVADO
THAT I CHOSE TO PUT ON
FOR THE CITIZENS AND HUMANS
IN THE FACE OF HARDSHIP
IS WHAT CAUSED YOU TO SUFFER.
NO, I DIDN'T JUST
CAUSE YOUR SUFFERING.
I BROUGHT ANGUISH
TO ALL OF THE FAMILIES
I TOOK EGGS FROM
SIX YEARS AGO.
NOW YOU UNDERSTAND.
THAT IS WHY I HANDED
THE SWORD TO YOU.
I SWEAR THAT EXCEED KIND
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
IT WAS MY FAULT ALONE.
- ( crying )
OH, MEOW!
- IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT,
YOUR MAJESTY.
NO ONE IS TO BLAME.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE
HELD RESPONSIBLE
WHEN YOU WERE ONLY DOING
WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS BEST
FOR THE CITIZENS
OF EXTALIA.
- YEAH, WE'RE JUST AS MUCH
TO BLAME AS YOU ARE,
QUEEN CHAGOT, 'CAUSE WE
WERE SO FULL OF OURSELVES.
- BUT NOW THAT
WE'RE IN EARTH LAND,
WE CAN MAKE
THINGS RIGHT AGAIN.
- LET'S GO OUT THERE AND
FIND ALL THE EXCEED CHILDREN
THAT WERE SENT AWAY
SIX YEARS AGO.
- ( Exceed cheering )
- THIS IS AWESOME.
WE'VE GOT NEW PURPOSE!
- LET'S DO OUR BEST
TO BECOME FRIENDS
WITH THE HUMANS.
- HERE'S TO MAKING
A FRESH START, YOU GUYS.
- ( giggles ) THEY'RE
OPTIMISTIC, AREN'T THEY?
- THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
- ( cheers ) - WE SHOULD
ALL COUNT OUR BLESSINGS TODAY.
WE ARE LUCKY TO BE GRANTED
THIS NEW BEGINNING.
- WELL, OKAY.
THEN, IN THAT CASE,
I FORGIVE YOU.
- OH.
CARLA.
- BUT TELL ME
HOW DID I END UP
POSSESSING THE SAME
PROPHETIC POWER THAT YOU DO?
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
TO SAY. - ( coughing )
- WELL, THIS IS AWKWARD.
- ISN'T THE WEATHER LOVELY?
- WHY ARE YOU AVOIDING
MY QUESTION?
- CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- YEAH?
- IS IT JUST ME OR
DO QUEEN CHAGOT AND CARLA
LOOK A LOT ALIKE?
- YOU THINK SO?
- AYE, SIR.
ALSO, THEY ACT THE SAME.
- THEY DO?
- ( laughs )
- Happy: YEAH!
THEY DO ALL
THE SAME STUFF?
- Lucky: GAH!
GUESS I NEVER NOTICED.
- IT ALL WORKED OUT.
I'M GLAD EVERYTHING
ENDED UP OKAY.
- YES.
- THAT'S FUNNY.
YOU TOTALLY CAUGHT
HIS WEIRD ARM WAVING.
- SO HAVE YOU, GRAY.
- SNIFF, SNIFF, SNIFF.
- ( gasps )
- AREN'T YOU LOVELY?
SUCH A FRAGRANT PARFUM!
MHMM, I JUST
CAN'T GET ENOUGH!
- KNOCK IT OFF!
- PLEASE, MISS.
ALLOW ME TO ENJOY YOUR PARFUM
A LITTLE LONGER!
- NO, STOP IT!
GET AWAY!
- ( groans )
SO LOVELY,
YET SO CRUEL.
- I'M SORRY.
YOU JUST REMINDED ME
OF A VERY FORWARD ACQUAINTANCE.
- I THINK IT WOULD BE
BEST FOR US
TO TAKE UP RESIDENCE
SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
DON'T YOU? - YEAH, THEN
WE CAN VISIT EACH OTHER.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU SO CHIPPER ABOUT?
- CARLA.
NOW WE'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE EACH OTHER
WHENEVER WE WANT.
- WAIT.
SHE'S SO WARM.
- FEEL FREE TO COME AND
VISIT US ANYTIME, OKAY?
- AYE, AYE.
- GAH!
YOU DON'T
HAVE TO VISIT, SEE?!
- OH, I PROMISE YOU
I WILL.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT I REALLY LIKE
THE WAY THAT
THE TWO OF YOU SMELL.
- ( whimpers )
- ( giggles )
- ( screams ) - IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN SHOW UP UNANNOUNCED,
YOU GOT ANOTHER
THING COMING!
BE POLITE! AND CHECK WITH
US BEFORE YOU VISIT!
YOU'RE NOT TOO OLD FOR ME
TO BEND YOU OVER MY KNEE!
- Exceeds: THANK YOU.
( chatter )
- BYE, WE'LL SEE YOU LATER!
- YEAH, TAKE CARE.
- BYE, FOR NOW.
- GOOD-BYE, I CAN'T THANK
YOU ENOUGH FOR EVERYTHING.
- GAH! I CAN'T
TAKE MUCH MORE
OF THIS MUSHY CRAP.
- YES, YES, I KNOW, DEAR.
- WE'LL COME BACK AND VISIT.
- BYE-BYE.
DON'T BE STRANGERS.
- ( giggling )
BYE-BYE.
- WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
- BYE-BYE.
- I'LL MISS YOUR SWEET PARFUM.
- THANKS AGAIN.
- ( laughs )
- Lucky: GAH!
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DIDN'T
JUST TELL CARLA
YOU'RE HER MOM.
- UNTIL WE CAN FIND
ALL OF THE CHILDREN
WE SENT TO EARTH LAND
SIX YEARS AGO,
I'M NOT FIT TO
CALL MYSELF A MOTHER.
I COULD ASK YOU
THE SAME THING?
- GAH! YOU GOT
TO BE KIDDING ME.
I DON'T NEED
NO SON THAT BLUE!
- I'M JUST GLAD WE CAN SEE HIM
WHENEVER WE WANT.
- THAT MAY SEEM
LIKE A GOOD THING,
BUT WAIT TILL
HE'S OVER ALL THE TIME.
I GOT TO SAY, QUEEN CHAGOT,
I HAD NO IDEA
THAT YOU'D SENT
YOUR OWN DAUGHTER
TO EARTH LAND TOO.
- I AM MERELY A WOMAN
WHO WAS NAMED A QUEEN.
AND JUST LIKE YOU,
I KNOW HOW MUCH CHILDREN
MEAN TO THEIR PARENTS.
- Lucky: GAH!
AIN'T THAT THE TRUTH.
- ( Marl laughs )
- ALL RIGHTY!
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE HEAD BACK TO THE GUILD?
- SOUNDS GOOD, BUT WHAT ARE
WE GONNA TELL EVERYONE?
- NOTHING.  SINCE THEY GOT
NO CLUE THAT ANYTHING HAPPENED,
WHY BOTHER TELLING THEM?
- THAT'S A GOOD POINT,
BUT I THINK WE SHOULD
TELL THEM ABOUT MYSTOGAN,
DON'T YOU? -
HEY, WHAT'S WITH YOUR ARMS?
- UH, WE GOT A PROBLEM.
- IT AIN'T A PROBLEM!
IT'S ACTUALLY A LOT OF FUN.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
- YEAH, COME ON, DO IT.
- I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
YOUR FIST PUMPING,
YOU MORONS!
WHERE THE HECK IS MY CAT?!
DON'T TELL ME THOSE
FLYING FELINES
TOOK LILY WITH THEM?!
- WHO IS LILY?
- REMEMBER THAT BIG,
BRAWNY EXCEED WHO HELPED US?
- ARE YOU BLIND?
I'M RIGHT HERE.
- All: SO TINY!
- YOU LOOK REALLY CUTE
THAT SIZE, THOUGH.
- UNFORTUNATELY, IT APPEARS
MY PREVIOUS PHYSIQUE
WASN'T WELL-SUITED
FOR EARTH LAND.
- OBVIOUSLY.
AND THAT DOESN'T BOTHER YOU?
- WELL, NORMALLY IT WOULD, YES.
BUT RIGHT NOW,
I WANT TO JOIN THE GUILD
THAT TOOK CARE
OF MY PRINCE.
YOU PROMISED ME.
YOU SAID YOU'D
GET ME IN, GAJEEL.
CAN YOU?
- HE HE!
CONSIDER IT DONE, BUDDY!
WELCOME TO FAIRY TAIL.
- WHOA.
HE'S CRYING?!
- NOW, ON AN UNRELATED NOTE,
I HAPPENED TO COME ACROSS
A SUSPICIOUS PERSON.
- WHAT AN OVERACHIEVER.
YOU'RE DEFINITELY MY CAT,
ALL RIGHT.
- Pantherlily: COME HERE.
- ( girl grunts )
HOLD ON!
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
PLEASE LET ME EXPLAIN.
OWW, THAT HURT.
- ( gasps )
- I'M NOT SUSPICIOUS.
I'M A MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL TOO.
- ( gasps )
IT'S LISANNA.
- DON'T BE SO
ROUGH WITH ME, CAT!
WAIT, ARE YOU AN EXCEED?
- THE NAME IS PANTHERLILY.
- IF YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH MY CAT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO
TAKE IT UP WITH ME, LADY!
WELL?! -
WHOA, SHE LOOKS JUST LIKE--
- LISANNA!
- NO WAY.
- IT CAN'T BE.
PERHAPS SHE'S THE ONE
FROM EDOLAS?
- HOW IN THE WORLD
DID SHE END UP HERE?
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- NATSU!
( giggles )
- ( gasping )
- NATSU, IT'S YOU.
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER
SEE YOU AGAIN.
- OH, HAPPY!
YOU'RE HERE TOO.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE I'VE SEEN EVERYONE.
THIS MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
- OH, YOU MUST BE THE TWO
NEW MEMBERS OF THE GUILD
I HAVEN'T MET YET.
THE LITTLE ONE
LOOKS LIKE WENDY.
AND THE BLONDE MUST BE LUCY.
- WAIT A SEC--
YOU-- ARE YOU...
OUR LISANNA?
- HM-HMM.
- ( gasping )
- FOR REAL?!
- ( gasps )
- SHE CAME BACK TO LIFE!
- HURRAY!
- ( both grunt )
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
YOU CAN'T BE OUR LISANNA.
SHE DIED TWO YEARS AGO.
AND SHE COULDN'T POSSIBLY
HAVE BEEN RESUSCITATED.
- THE TRUTH IS I DIDN'T
ACTUALLY DIE THAT DAY.
- ( gasping )
- TWO YEARS AGO...
- Mirajane: LISANNA!
YOU HAVE
TO WAKE UP, LISANNA!
NO, WHY ARE YOU GLOWING?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
NO, DON'T LEAVE ME!
( cries )
YOU CAN'T DISAPPEAR ON ME!
PLEASE DON'T GO, LISANNA!
STAY HERE WITH ME!
( screams )
- Lisanna: AT THAT MOMENT,
I MUST HAVE SUDDENLY BEEN
PULLED AWAY BY AN ANIMA.
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I ASSUME
THERE WERE LITTLE ONES
ALL OVER EARTH LAND
BACK IN THOSE DAYS.
IT WAS A REAL SHOCK
WHEN I AWOKE IN EDOLAS.
IT'S MY GUILD.
- ( whispering )
- Lisanna: I WAS CONFUSED
BECAUSE EVERYONE
LOOKED SO DIFFERENT.
BUT I RECOGNIZED
ALL OF THE PEOPLE THERE.
THEY WELCOMED ME BECAUSE
THEY THOUGHT
I WAS THE EDOLAS
FAIRY TAIL'S LISANNA.
I CAN ONLY ASSUME
THAT SHE DIED.
EVERYONE SEEMED SO
SURPRISED TO SEE ME.
IT WAS AS THOUGH
I'D COME BACK FROM THE DEAD.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
LISANNA'S COME BACK TO US.
- TO THINK SHE SURVIVED
THAT TERRIBLE FALL.
I THOUGHT I'D
NEVER SEE HER AGAIN.
- ( gasps )
I WAS THOROUGHLY CONFUSED
AT THE TIME.
BUT LOOKING BACK ON IT,
I THINK I UNDERSTAND WHY
THE ANIMA PULLED ME IN.
IT WAS SIMPLY TRYING
TO FILL A VOID IN EDOLAS,
A VOID THAT WAS CAUSED
BY THE OTHER LISANNA'S DEATH.
- PLEASE DON'T EVER
LEAVE US AGAIN, OKAY?
- ( cries )
LISANNA!
- DON'T CRY.
I'M HERE.
I COULDN'T FIND IT IN MY HEART
TO TELL THEM THE TRUTH.
SO I PRETENDED
TO BE EDOLAS'S LISANNA.
( echoes )
I'M HOME.
THERE WAS SOME
CONFUSION AT FIRST.
I WOULD APOLOGIZE AND
TELL THEM MY MEMORY WAS HAZY.
I TRIED MY BEST TO FIT IN
AND IT GOT EASIER
AS I LEARNED MORE ABOUT EDOLAS.
IT DIDN'T TAKE VERY LONG
TO GET ACCUSTOMED
TO MY NEW LIFE THERE.
TWO YEARS PASSED QUICKLY.
AND THEN NATSU AND HAPPY
SHOWED UP OUT OF THE BLUE
SIX DAYS AGO.
- WHY, LISANNA?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU DIDN'T BOTHER
TO TELL US THE TRUTH THEN?!
- IT WASN'T THE RIGHT TIME.
- LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU GUYS
ARE FROM ANOTHER WORLD
THAT'S CALLED EARTH LAND?
- HEY, LISANNA,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S NATSU-- THE NATSU
AND HAPPY THAT I KNOW.
I CAN'T LET THEM FIND OUT.
I DON'T WANT MY POOR
BROTHER AND SISTER
TO GO THROUGH
THAT SADNESS AGAIN.
( cries )
I HAVE TO BE STRONG.
I HAVE TO LIVE
MY LIFE IN EDOLAS.
BUT THEN...
- WHOA, WHAT'S
HAPPENING TO YOU?
- YOUR BODY, IT'S GLOWING.
- UM, IT'S NOT
WHAT YOU THINK.
- ( gasps )
- I'M SORRY.
- IT'S FINE.
WE'VE KNOWN ALL ALONG.
- WE JUST WANTED MORE TIME
WITH OUR LITTLE SISTER.
FORGIVE US.
- YOU'RE A SWEET GIRL,
JUST AS SWEET
AS OUR LISANNA.
BUT YOU HAVE TO GO.
I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOUR REAL
BROTHER AND SISTER
CARE ABOUT ABOUT YOU.
SO PLEASE DON'T MAKE
THEM SUFFER ANY MORE.
- BUT I...
CARE ABOUT YOU TOO.
- YOU STILL HAVE YOUR
SIBLINGS IN EARTH LAND.
GO TO THEM.
PLEASE GIVE THEM
OUR REGARDS.
WE'LL MISS YOU.
- ( screams )
- Narrator:
THE KARDIA CATHEDRAL
IN EARTH LAND.
- COME ON, SIS.
LET'S GET YOU
OUT OF THE RAIN.
- GIVE ME A SECOND.
- MIRA!
- ( gasps )
- MIRA, IT'S ME!
HEY, BIG BROTHER ELF!
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
IS THIS REAL?
- ( laughs )
- ( sobs )
- LISANNA.
( cries )
- ( all cry )
- I'M BACK, SIS.
- ( gasping )
- WELCOME HOME.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: OKAY, THAT'S WEIRD.
WHERE THE HECK DID IT GO?
- Happy: IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG?
- I HAD A SPECIAL SNACK
THAT I WAS SAVING
FOR TODAY, BUT NOW IT'S GONE.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR LEAVING IT OUT,
YOU BIG DUMMY.
SO WHAT WAS IT, ANYWAY?
- WELL, I HAD SOME
LEFTOVER FIRE YESTERDAY
SO I PUT IT IN A CAN.
BUT I JUST LOOKED INSIDE
AND IT'S EMPTY.
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
MIRA PUT IT OUT
BECAUSE SHE WAS WORRIED
THE GUILD HALL
WOULD CATCH ON FIRE.
- OH, SHE DID, DID SHE?
- SORRY,
BUT I THINK SHE'S IN
THE RIGHT HERE, NATSU.