[LUCY sighs]
Aw. Don't let it
get you down, Lucy.
I'm sure you can find
out what it means.
Mmm. Well it
won't be easy.
We've taken a
new job request.
[GRAY] There are some
bad guys stealing gold
that we need to catch.
I hope it's not the
Butt Jiggle Gang again.
[GRAY] Whoever it is,
we gotta put a stop to 'em.
Sorry, but I'm gonna
pass on this one.
We're having a hard
time getting very far
on figuring out what
this inscription says.
Where's Natsu?
[LUCY] No clue, I think
he took off a while ago.
Well, if that's the case,
then we'll be leaving.
Cool.
Wait. Hang on a sec.
When you say "we"
are you talking about
just the two of us going?
Do you have a
problem with that?
[GRAY] A-A problem?
Of course not.
If we hurry, we may be
back before nightfall.
So let's move.
[JUVIA] This is a
major problem, Gray!
You should have insisted
that I come along with you!
How could my
darling be so cruel?
This is so boring.
Come on, it's a matter of
'lunch or death' here Natsu.
How can anyone
be bored by that?
Okay, I'll snap out
of it, I promise.
Are you kidding me?
What do you want?
[GORIAN chuckles]
I was just thinking
about how much I wanna
settle the score with
those Fairy Tail losers.
And all of a sudden one
of 'em walks on my turf.
Monkey's got
a bone to pick?
Yeah, I gotta pick which
one I wanna break first.
I think I'll start
with your face.
You're in for the
shock of your life.
[GORIAN screams]
No way.
I know what that means.
Huh? What're ya
talkin' about?
Laxus is here.
What?
I'm positive
it's him.
I was wondering where
he had run off to,
I guess he picked
the wrong neighborhood.
But master didn't let him get
back into the guild, did he?
I wonder what he's
doing around here.
I'm gonna find out!
[HAPPY] Hey, Natsu!
Wait for me!
[HAPPY] Turbulent Showdown!
Natsu vs. Laxus!
[NATSU] What's up, metal head?
[GAJEEL] None of your
business, flame brain!
Are you going somewhere?
Why? Are you?
I asked you first,
didn't I?
Yeah? Who cares?
You ain't following me!
I don't wanna,
so get lost!
Would you two cut
it out already?
We need to go
see what that
random lightning
strike was about!
What?
I already told you it
was Laxus, didn't I?
I'm gonna go put the
smack down on him!
Please.
You don't have a snowball's
chance in hell against him.
Remember last time?
Even with me giving you
a major helping hand,
he still beat the
ever-lovin' snot outta ya.
[GAJEEL chuckles]
Chuckle all you want, but
I didn't need your help then,
and I don't
need it this time!
I'll beat him with
my own two hands!
Not if I get
to him first!
[LAXUS]
Who's beatin' who, again?
[NATSU and GAJEEL] Laxus?
Whoa!
That lightning really
was him, after all.
[BIXLOW, EVERGREEN,
and FRIED] Laxus!
It would seem that
he's not alone, either.
What's going on?
There's nothing goin'
on here, is there?
Have you been living out in
the woods this entire time?
[LAXUS] Heh.
I traveled around
quite a bit,
but I've been here
for a little while.
If you're this close,
you should just
come back to
the guild already.
Why's that, have you
been missing me?
[NATSU] I don't give a crap
if you come back or not.
But since we're here,
I think we should
throw down and see
who comes out on top.
Sounds good to me.
Heh. You guys really want me
to take the bait, don't ya?
You wanna go and get me all
riled up and ready to fight.
Well I got better
things to do.
Like run away?
What?
You've never been
the type of guy
who backed down
from a challenge.
So what're
you scared of?
You'd be wise to mind
your tongue, Natsu.
[GAJEEL] Heh, heh.
[LAXUS sighs]
Okay, fine.
Now that's more like it!
Sorry, but you ain't
layin' a finger on him.
You'll have to go through
the Thunder Legion.
Laxus' fate and our own shall
never again be torn asunder!
No, I'd actually love
to teach these two clowns
a lesson all by myself.
Sounds like fun to me!
All right, Natsu.
Guess you're
first in line.
[WENDY] Wait! Hold on!
Huh? What for?
If you guys are really
gonna go through with this,
you gotta make sure that
it's a special occasion!
I don't follow you.
What are you
talkin' about?
The match will take
place tomorrow!
Okay, if you insist,
have it your way.
I can wait one more day
to kick his butt!
Meet me tomorrow under the big
Sola tree in South Gate Park!
And when he's done,
it'll be my turn.
Sounds like a plan to me.
[WENDY sighs]
[WAKABA] You guys hear
about the big showdown?
Add that one to the list
of Natsu's bad decisions.
Did you know
Laxus was around?
He's been living in the woods
around Magnolia for a while.
Big time fights
are so manly.
This is gonna be
the best one ever!
Should we be worried about
Natsu and Gajeel getting hurt?
Oh, they're gonna
get hurt, alright.
Yeah. Laxus is not someone
I'd ever want to go up against.
Those two don't stand
a chance against him.
Is he really that much
stronger than them?
He's a tough
customer for sure.
Back when he was still a
member, I'd say that probably
the only one more powerful
than him was Gildarts.
Okay!
As the master of the guild, I'd
better get this party started!
Yeah! It'll be
a fight party!
The manliest
kind there is!
That's a great idea.
Turn this into something
fun for everyone!
[GROUP] Alright!
[NATSU] This is crazy.
What's going on here?
Is there some kinda festival
happening or somethin'?
[HAPPY] Everyone's
gettin' their party on!
You do realize that this
is all because of you?
How so?
I'm having so much fun, and
all of the food is wonderful!
Geez, does she have a
hollow leg or something?
[HAPPY] Seriously,
what's the festival for?
[LUCY] I'm being serious.
It's because people heard
about the big fight.
[MICHELLE] And they
decided to put together
a festival the night before.
Huh...
Magnolia sure does
love to party!
Well, I know you probably
don't care, but we weren't
getting anywhere figuring out
that ancient language.
So this seemed like a good
way to unwind for a bit.
I'm getting
hungry again!
Heh, heh, heh.
I can hardly believe it.
Oh so cool!
Ladies and gentlemen,
it has been too long!
But your favorite reporter,
Jason, is back!
It's a reunion seven
years in the making!
And what a cool
way to celebrate!
Because this is gonna
be the most insane,
awesome fight in the
history of fighting!
Get off the stage!
It's time for you to bring out
the real talent already!
Without further ado,
I'm honored to announce a woman
that is the very
definition of beauty!
The lovely and super
talented Miss Mirajane!
[MIRAJANE] Woo!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
Are you boys and
girls ready to rock?
Bring it on, Big Sis!
Light up the
stage, Mira!
Well, I hate to
break it to you,
but my poor throat has been
feeling awfully sore all day.
[AUDIENCE] Aww...
[HAPPY] Hey Natsu, don't you
think it'd be a good idea
to at least do a little
training before the big fight?
That won't be necessary.
I was just planning
on hitting him hard
with everything
I've already got.
Of course.
Why would I ever think
that you would have any
real strategy in mind?
I wonder how Gajeel's
gearing up for the showdown.
[NATSU] You know he's gotta be
really afraid he'll get beaten.
So he's probably somewhere
doing some kind of
super crazy training.
Instead, let me introduce a
singer who's got soul and style.
A true, one-of-a-kind performer
like you've never seen.
Put your hands together!
[guitar feedback]
What the heck is
he doin' up there?
Doesn't look
like training!
[strums guitar]
Thanks folks.
I appreciate you comin'
out to see me tonight.
I didn't come to
see this crap.
By special request,
I'd like to start with a little
ditty I wrote myself.
You tryin' to tell me someone
actually asked for this?
I call it "Best Friend."
Here we go.
Doesn't he know
any other songs?
♪ You're sparkling, and
colorful shoo-bee-doo-ba! ♪
♪ You caught my eye.
Like a shiny piece of metal. ♪
Um, I don't know if I like this
side of Gajeel all that much.
His singing is pretty bad.
He's super bad!
Oh my gosh, Levy!
You're back in town!
Yeah.
Team Shadow Gear and I took on
our first gig in like, forever.
You're just in time;
I need your beautiful brain
to translate an
ancient inscription.
[GAJEEL howls]
[GAJEEL]
Thank you, Magnolia!
[GRAY] Looks like we're
camping out tonight.
There goes making it
home before nightfall.
At least we were able
to locate their hideout.
Now all we need to do is
wait for them to return
with the stolen
gold in hand.
Yeah, you're right.
[GRAY] Man, so now what?
Being stuck alone with
Erza is so awkward.
I never know what
to do or talk about.
What's wrong?
[GRAY] Hm?
You're not stripping.
What?
I would assume you'd feel more
comfortable sleeping naked.
[JUVIA] Ahh! I knew all she
wanted was to steal him away!
Well, uh, kinda
depends on my mood.
I mean, you're still just
hanging out in full armor.
You make a valid
point, I suppose.
Gray...
Sleep?
[GRAY] Yeah, sure.
[JUVIA] I can't believe she's so
forward and demanding like that!
I thought she was more of a
lady, not some boy-crazed hussy!
Gray is complex
and sensitive.
He needs a more tender
and loving approach.
Bed time. My darling.
Juvie!
[JUVIA] Focus! Focus!
I can't let my imagination
run wild at a time like this!
[GRAY] Wow, she fell
asleep right away.
How can she even
get comfortable?
[ERZA grunts]
[GRAY] Seeing her all
peaceful and quiet like this,
makes me realize
how pretty she is.
They've returned.
Looks like it.
[ERZA] Let's go.
[GRAY] Yeah.
[JUVIA] He was tested,
but I knew my darling Gray
was saving himself for me!
[ERZA] Stop right there!
[BANDIT 129A] Yeah? Says who?
I'm Erza Scarlet, a
wizard from Fairy Tail.
You didn't really have
to take the question
so literally,
ya know?
We've been sent
here to recover
what you've stolen
from our client.
Resistance is futile.
Now hand over the
gold immediately!
[BANDIT 129A] Ha, ha, ha! We
thought they might send someone.
So we hired ourselves
some bodyguards.
Alright guys. We're giving you
a pretty big chunk of the loot,
so you'd better deal
with these Fairy pests.
Nice night
for a battle.
Too bad you're up against
the Vanish Brothers.
Let's make this quick.
[ERZA] So you're
the Vanish Brothers.
I've heard about you before.
[GRAY] Yeah, me too.
These are the same guys that
Natsu beat the crap out of
at Duke Everlue's place.
You're talkin' about
ancient history, pal.
We've been training
non-stop since that day.
At the level we're at now,
taking on the mighty
Erza Scarlet sounds like
a walk in the park.
[ERZA] I've often wondered
about mercenary guilds.
How much power could one have
with no loyalty whatsoever?
[GRAY] Let me handle
these guys by myself.
Oh yeah?
Natsu didn't have
a problem with it.
So I'm sure it'll be
just as easy for me.
Big bro, I think this
guy's mocking us.
You shouldn't
let it get to you.
Remember this
is just business,
so there's no need to
take things personally.
And our job is to cave
in his skull, right?
Yes, so let's
get to work.
I'll put you on ice.
It seems this one
is an ice wizard.
Although my frying pan
is perfectly suited
to absorb fire attacks,
I'm sure ice will prove
to be even easier.
[GRAY] Ice Make Lance!
It will trap it,
double its strength
and send it right
back to you!
You think you can
hit me with that?
Impressive.
Let's give him
double trouble!
[BALD BROTHER] Heaven and Earth
Annihilation Technique!
Look toward heaven, and
we strike from the earth!
[GRAY grunts]
[HAIR BROTHER]
Look towards earth,
and we strike down from Heaven!
[GRAY yells]
Very few have survived.
Our ultimate
combination attack.
[GRAY yells]
[ERZA] Natsu may have
defeated them once,
but that was over
seven years ago.
Perhaps they truly
have improved.
[JUVIA] Don't worry, my dear.
I will save you.
I got this, okay!
[GRAY] You talk a big game.
But I feel just fine!
[BROTHERS] Nonsense!
Prepare to die!
You got heaven and earth but
let me show ya what I got!
Ice Bringer!
Not a chance!
[BALD BROTHER yells]
[JUVIA] He's just so amazing!
[GRAY sighs]
[ERZA] Gray has improved
over the years as well.
I'm surprised you took
that long to beat them.
I wanted to have
a little fun, too.
You will return every ounce of
gold you stole from our client!
Do I make myself clear?
[BANDITS] Yes ma'am.
Crystal clear!
[JUVIA] I can go home
knowing my love is safe!
[LAXUS] What's the big occasion?
When word got out that
you were havin' a fight,
the whole town decided
to throw a big party.
You seeing
this, Laxus?
You're still quite the
celebrity around here.
Yeah, I see they're all
still a bunch of idiots.
You're a true legend
of the Fairy Tail guild.
So why don't you
realize how much
we all desperately
need you...
Get a hold of
yourself, man.
[BOY 129A laughs]
Thanks a lot, grandpa!
[OLD MAN 129A] Sure, but
don't tell your mom, okay?
[WENDY] This is horrible.
The only reason I told them
to wait a day is so they could
calm down a little bit
and call off the fight.
[CARLA] It seems your plan
may have backfired, child.
I never thought it'd turn
into such a big deal.
[MAKAROV] Something
troubling you, Wendy?
[WENDY] Actually, there is.
Where have you
been hiding yourself,
we've been looking
everywhere for you!
Why, has something
happened?
Natsu and Gajeel
are in trouble.
They're about to have
fight against Laxus!
They're doing what?
[JASON] Cool!
Laxus is so calm and
collected, it's terrifying!
Sweet!
Black Steel Gajeel is
ready to throw down!
The two heroes stare
down their opponent.
The tension is so thick
you can cut it with a knife!
[GAJEEL chuckles]
[JASON] Natsu has arrived!
All three warriors
are in their places!
Now check
this out, Happy.
Aye, sir!
[JASON] Laxus stands up!
Looks like Natsu is
getting first crack at him!
Let's do this thing.
[NATSU] Bring it!
But I gotta warn you, that
I'm not gonna hold back!
I don't blame ya.
You understand?
If you don't survive this,
it ain't my fault.
I could say the same
for you, big guy!
You'd better
get back, Happy.
Good luck, Natsu,
I'm rooting for ya!
[NATSU] Thanks, pal.
[AUDIENCE gasps]
[JASON] Yes, it's on now!
[NATSU yells]
[MACAO] This is
gonna be intense!
[PANTHERLILY] Whoever
strikes first will lose.
[NATSU yells]
[CROWD] Whoa!
[gasps]
T-K-O!
[bell rings]
[MACAO and WAKABA laugh]
The poor kid didn't
land a single hit!
I don't know
about that,
he hit the ground
pretty dang hard.
Are you okay?
Great job as
usual, Laxus!
The little guy's still
got nothin' on ya, buddy.
So are you ready
for round two?
He's gone.
Whoa! Gajeel just ghosted!
Ya' mean that lousy
coward ran away?
[PANTHERLILY] What?
Alright you guys,
let's track him down!
It's a manhunt!
That sounds so manly!
I always thought you had
the heart of a warrior, Gajeel!
Are you even able
to stand up, Natsu?
[LEVY] Oh sweet!
This is written in
ancient Potamelian!
[MICHELLE] I've never
heard of that.
So, now that you've
figured that out,
do you know
what it says?
"Time ticks forward on
toward inevitable chaos."
"Time ticks forward."
"On toward inevitable chaos?"
Sounds familiar.
I know I've heard
it somewhere before.
You have?
Hm... yeah.
But where?
You're just gonna
take off again?
[EVERGREEN] Please!
Come back to Fairy Tail!
Master!
Hasn't his expulsion from
the guild lasted long enough?
Take him back!
It's not this one or this.
Here it is! I found it!
It's in here.
That spooky phrase.
I was sure that I had
read it somewhere before
and it's in this book.
[LEVY] What's the book about?
Well, lemme see.
Basically, it's about an
old clock that passes from
one owner to the next over
a long period of time,
and a lot of mysterious
things happen around it
throughout its history.
Whoa, I think
I get it, guys.
What do you mean?
Check out
this picture.
[MICHELLE gasps]
[LUCY] This isn't just
some random object.
It's the hand of a clock.
[HAPPY] He rattled
your brains, huh?
[NATSU groans]
Nah, I've had much
worse headaches.
I wonder where that scaredy-cat
Gajeel is hiding himself.
Macao and the others went
out looking for him.
But no one knows where he is.
Hm?
I think I can hear
Gajeel outside.
[PANTHERLILY]
Where have you been?
[CARLA and HAPPY gasp]
I don't believe it.
[NATSU] What the heck?
Who could be dumb enough to
pick a fight with Fairy Tail?
Wait, do these guys
seem familiar to you?
[HAPPY] Geez, you must
need glasses Natsu.
These are the same jokers that
we went up against in Edolas.
[NATSU] No way!
Did they always look like this?
[HAPPY] Um. Now that
you mention it,
they do look
pretty different.
[NATSU] Guess I'm not the
only one who needs glasses.
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next Time: Target: Lucy!
[HAPPY] Hold on, are they
going after Lucy? Why?
[NATSU] Well, that's
really nothing new,
someone's always
out to get her.
[HAPPY] I bet she probably
forgot to pay her rent again.