- HEY, GUYS!  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV!
- YOU CAN SAY YOUR PRAYERS,
BUT YOU'RE STILL GONNA BURN
IN HELL TONIGHT!
OH, YEAH!
ARE YOU READY TO ROCK?
- JUVIA.
WHAT DID THAT GUY DO TO HER?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ROCK ON!
- ( rock music playing )
- COME ON!  FEEL THE NOISE!
- IT'S SO LOUD!
JUVIA, IS ALL THIS NOISE MAKING
YOU ACT LIKE THIS?
- HA HA HA!
- DON'T WASTE YOUR BREATH!
MY SUCCUBUS SPELL MADE THIS
GLOOMY GROUPIE HERE MY SLAVE!
I GOT HER LIKE A DOG
ON A CHAIN. ( laughs )
YEAH, I THOUGHT ABOUT MAKING
BOTH OF YOU BABES MY SLAVES,
BUT THAT WOULDN'T BE
AS MUCH FUN.
'CAUSE THERE'S NOTHING HOTTER
THAN WATCHING CHICKS
IN A CATFIGHT.
GIVE ME SOME HAIR PULLING,
CLOTHES RIPPING,
DOWN AND DIRTY ACTION.
- YOU'RE A REAL SICKO.
- OH, YEAH?
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO SWEET TALK ME,
DON'T YOU, BABY?   HA HA!
- THAT LITTLE BABY IS ABOUT
TO GET THE SPANKING OF HER LIFE.
- AWW, MAN.
I JUST CHANGED CLOTHES.
- NOW THEN.
- ( gasps )
- WE NEED TO WORK ON YOUR IMAGE
IF YOU REALLY WANNA ROCK.
YOU GOTTA START BY SHOWING
A LITTLE MORE SKIN.  LIKE THIS.
- ( screaming )
- ( Happy speaking )
- OH, YEAH! I'M BAD
TO THE BONE. ( laughing )
- HA HA!
- DON'T LET HIM GET TO YOU.
YOU'VE GOTTA SNAP OUT OF IT,
JUVIA.
- (grunts)
- AH!
( grunts )
LISTEN.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO JOIN FAIRY
TAIL LIKE YOU SAID YOU DID,
THIS ISN'T THE BEST WAY
TO GO ABOUT GETTING IN.
- NOW WE'RE REALLY ROCKING, BUT
I NEED MORE SCREAMS IN THE MIX.
CRANK SOME OUT FOR ME.
- ( screaming )
- WATER CANE!
- YEAH, THAT'S THE SOUND THAT
SETS MY EARS ON FIRE.
REAL HARDCORE ROCK AND ROLL.
- YOU LIKE THAT?
- HA HA! DON'T PUT THE BRAKES
ON THE CATFIGHT, GIRLS.
GET NASTY LIKE YOU'RE
FIGHTING OVER A DUDE
THAT ROCKS YOUR WORLD.
- SHE WANTS MY MAN.
- HUH?
- SHE'S MY RIVAL.
- NO, I'M NOT!
THIS IS HOPELESS.
HE HAS COMPLETE CONTROL
OVER HER.
I'VE GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
THERE'S NO WAY I COULD BEAT
JUVIA IN A REAL FIGHT.
SHE'S TOO STRONG.
- ( laughing )
YOU'RE GONNA DROWN IN MY BODY
OF WATER.
- I CAN'T HOLD MY BREATH
MUCH LONGER.
- LUCY, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- JUVIA?
- I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T CONTROL MY ACTIONS.
- IT'S LIKE SHE'S IN MY HEAD.
- I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU
BECAUSE I CONSIDER YOU A FRIEND.
AND I HOPE THAT YOU THINK
OF ME AS ONE, TOO.
I KNOW WE'VE HAD OUR FAIR SHARE
OF ARGUMENTS
BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH MADLY
IN LOVE WITH GRAY.
- YEAH.  NO.
- BUT I REALLY DO LIKE YOU.
I'VE GROWN TO LOVE EVERYONE
I'VE MET IN FAIRY TAIL.
THEY CARE ABOUT OTHERS.
THEY LIKE TO HAVE FUN.
THEY'RE SO FRIENDLY AND WARM.
FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS ARE LIKE RAYS
OF SUNSHINE
THAT CHASE AWAY THE CLOUDS
ON A GLOOMY DAY.
BEFORE I MET ALL OF YOU,
I NEVER KNEW THAT A GUILD COULD
BE SUCH A HAPPY PLACE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
I FELT LIKE I WAS MAKING FRIENDS
THAT I COULD HONESTLY TRUST.
BUT WHO'D WANT TO BE FRIENDS
WITH A GIRL WHO WILL
BRING THEM MISFORTUNE?
- SHE'S CRYING.
EVEN IN ALL THIS WATER,
I CAN STILL FEEL THE WARMTH
OF HER TEARS.
- NOW. JUVIA.   IT'S TIME
FOR THE BIG FINALE, BABY!
- OH, YEAH.
YOU READY TO BE ROCKED?
- SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
SOMEONE WHO'D SHED TEARS FOR
THEIR FRIENDS
WILL ALWAYS BE WELCOME
IN THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
- LUCY.
- I KNOW YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
AND THANKS TO YOU,
I JUST HAD A GREAT IDEA.
- WHAT A LOAD OF CRAP.
LET'S SEND THIS BORING PRUDE
TO HELL ALREADY.
HIT IT, BABY.
- OH, I WILL.  MY WATER JIGSAW
WILL CUT YOU INTO LITTLE PIECES.
NO ENCORE FOR YOU.
YOU HAVE TO GET OUT
OF THE WAY, LUCY.
( screaming )
- ( grunts )
OPEN GATE OF THE WATER BEARER.
AQUARIUS!
- WHAT THE--
- SHE SUMMONED ONE OF HER
SPIRITS USING MY BODY?
- IF THERE'S WATER, I CAN ALWAYS
CALL ON THE MOST VICIOUS SPIRIT
I KNOW, AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO
THAT BODY OF YOURS. - ( gasps )
- I GET CALLED ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE FOR YOU ANNOYING COWS?
- SORRY.
- SO MUCH.
- WATER.
- WHAT DID I TELL YA? WATER'S
THE BEST THING FOR MY HAIR,
SO AS LONG AS IT'S FLOWING,
I'M GONNA KEEP SUCKING IT UP.
-  WHERE ARE YOU?
- ( gasps )
OVER HERE!
- JUVIA.
- LUCY.
- WHERE DID ALL THIS MAGIC
ENERGY COME FROM?
DON'T TELL ME THEY'VE
FUSED THEIR POWERS.
IT'S A UNISON RAID.
- WHOA!
THIS MIGHT BE A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
I WAS JUST KIDDING, LADIES,
YOU GOTTA TURN OFF THE
WATER NOW, PLEASE.
- ( screaming )
WICKED.
( gasps )
- ( gasping )
- WE WON!
- AND I'M NOT A GROUPIE ANYMORE.
- I'M SO GLAD.
THANKS FOR ALL OF YOUR HELP.
I SHOULD BE THANKING YOU, LUCY.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME ANOTHER
GIRL HAS EVER BEEN NICE TO ME.
IT'S ALMOST TOO GOOD
TO BE TRUE.
- ( grunts )
- ( all scream )
- LISTEN, GIRLY.
YOU'D BETTER WATCH WHERE YOU
SUMMON ME FROM HERE ON OUT.
'CAUSE IF I EVER FIND MYSELF
POPPING OUT OF A TOILET
IN A FILTHY PUBLIC RESTROOM,
YOU'RE AS GOOD AS DEAD.
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT, MA'AM.
- I'M GONNA HAVE NIGHTMARES NOW.
- SO DON'T GO GETTING
CREATIVE AGAIN, GOT IT?
- I WON'T.  I PROMISE.
- OH, I'LL BE GOING ON VACATION
WITH MY SEXY MAN.
SO DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT SUMMONING ME.
- YES, MA'AM.
- YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
WHEN YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
HA. LIKE THAT'LL HAPPEN.
- HEY, I'M SINGLE BY CHOICE.
- I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND
YOUR TRUE LOVE SOMEDAY.
- ( sighs )
YEAH, MAYBE SO.
- ( snoring )
- WE JUST TOOK DOWN A MEMBER
OF TRINITY RAVEN.
I BET YOU THAT CREEPY JELLAL GUY
NEVER EXPECTED THAT ONE.
- WELL, I DIDN'T DO MUCH OF
ANYTHING.  IT WAS ALL YOU, LUCY.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WE WORKED TOGETHER.
YOU WERE THERE TO HELP ME
WHEN I NEEDED IT THE MOST.
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS ARE SUPPOSED
TO DO FOR EACH OTHER.
IT MEANT A LOT TO ME.
SO FROM NOW ON, THAT'S HOW I'D
LIKE YOU TO THINK OF ME.
AS A FRIEND THAT YOU CAN COUNT
ON, IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
- ( sobbing )
JUST GREAT.
AS IF THERE'S NOT ENOUGH WATER
IN HERE ALREADY.
IT'S OKAY,
TEARS OF JOY ARE ALLOWED.
MAN, I'M TIRED.
HOW ABOUT WE JUST STAY HERE
AND REST FOR A BIT?
- THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I COULD USE A BREAK.
- A UNISON RAID.
THEY ACTUALLY DID IT.
MONKS HAVE TRAINED
FOR THEIR ENTIRE LIVES
TRYING TO ACHIEVE IT.
BUT EVEN THE MOST DISCIPLINED
WERE NEVER ABLE TO SUCCEED.
THAT WAS QUITE IMPRESSIVE,
EVEN IF IT WAS DUMB LUCK.
WELL, I'VE LEARNED MY LESSON.
I WON'T UNDERESTIMATE THE POWER
OF ERZA'S ALLIES AGAIN.
- ( laughs )
- REGARDING OUR DEBATE OVER
WHETHER OR NOT TO ATTACK
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN,
THE FINAL VOTE STANDS AT FOUR
IN FAVOR AND FIVE AGAINST.
THEREFORE, THE COUNCIL HAS
DECIDED AGAINST FIRING
THE ETHERION CANNON
AT THIS TIME.
- YOU FOOLS.
EXTREME THREATS CAN ONLY BE
COUNTERED WITH EXTREME MEASURES.
- WATCH YOUR MOUTH, SIEGRAIN.
WE HAVE MADE OUR FINAL DECISION.
WE BELIEVE IT IS POSSIBLE
TO REACH A PEACEFUL RESOLUTION.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU'RE WRONG.
WHILE WE'RE HERE WASTING OUR
BREATH DEBATING THE ISSUE,
JELLAL'S COMING CLOSER AND
CLOSER TO RESURRECTING THE DEAD.
I KNOW YOU'VE FELT IT.
THE NEGATIVE ENERGY
THAT'S BEEN SLOWLY SPREADING
ACROSS THE LAND.
IT'S BECAUSE OF THE MAN
HE'S ATTEMPTING TO BRING BACK
FROM THE GRAVE.
- AND WHO IS THAT?
- STOP BEATING AROUND THE BUSH
AND GET TO THE POINT.
- I DARED NOT SPEAK HIS NAME,
AFRAID ANY MENTION OF HIM
WOULD CAUSE WIDESPREAD PANIC
SHOULD WORD GET OUT.
BUT YOU'VE LEFT ME
NO OTHER CHOICE.
- JUST TELL US
WHO YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
- HE'S RESURRECTING ZEREF.
- AGH!
- THAT'S INCONCEIVABLE.
- AND YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY
CERTAIN OF THIS?  YOU'RE SURE?
- I AM.
I KNOW JELLAL'S MOTIVATIONS
ALL TOO WELL.
SUCH IS THE BOND BETWEEN TWINS.
I CALL FOR ANOTHER VOTE.
- HOO-HOO!
- AGH!
- FIRE DRAGON TALON.
- SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
- THAT OWL GUY IS GOING
HIT FOR HIT WITH NATSU.
- OF COURSE HE IS.
I'D EXPECT NOTHING LESS FROM A
MEMBER OF TRINITY RAVEN.
- HOO-HOO!  AND NOW
THE MIGHTY HAMMER OF JUSTICE
WILL FINALLY FALL UPON YOU.
MISSILE! ( laughs )
- WOW!
WAY TO MISS YOUR TARGET, DODO.
( grunts )
- AND UP IT GOES.
ARM HANDS NOW!
- ( screaming )
- AROUND THE WORLD YOU GO.
- HIS ATTACKS ARE SO BIZARRE.
- ( grunts )
- NO, SLOW DOWN.
- I KNOW MY OPPONENTS'
WEAKNESSES VERY WELL,
SALAMANDER.
- OH, NO.
IT'S TRANSPORTATION.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- NATSU GETS SUPER MOTION SICK.
- WEAKEN YOUR PREY BEFORE
YOU GO IN FOR THE KILL.
THAT'S THE FIRST RULE
OF HUNTING.
- ( screaming )
- NOW CAPTURE! HOO-HOO-HOO!
- HE'S EATING HIM
LIKE A SANDWICH.
- ERZA.
- DO IT AGAIN, CANA.
YOU MUST'VE READ THE CARDS WRONG
'CAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
TODAY'S MY LUCKY DAY.
- LOOK, I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING,
AND I DIDN'T READ 'EM WRONG.
IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY SO JUST DEAL
WITH IT, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
- WELL, I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
JEEZ!  I FELL INTO A DITCH
ON MY WAY HERE THIS MORNING.
AND NOW I CAN'T FIND MY STUPID
WALLET.  TODAY TOTALLY SUCKS!
- HUH?
- ( crowd murmuring )
- SOMEONE'S KID COME
WANDERING IN?
- SHE DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE SOME REGULAR KID
OFF THE STREET TO ME.
- THIS IS IT.  THE GUILD
GRANDPA ROB TOLD ME ABOUT.
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- YOU'RE HERE.
- AND WHAT IS IT DOING TO NATSU?
- HE SWALLOWED HIM WHOLE?
- MY PREY IS NOT ONLY TASTY,
BUT I GAIN THEIR MAGIC ENERGY
AS WELL.
- GIVE HIM BACK TO ME NOW.
- ( laughs )
FIRE!  HOO-HOO-HOO!
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- HAPPY?
- ( wincing )
- WHEN HE DEVOURED SALAMANDER,
HE SOMEHOW GAINED
HIS MAGIC POWERS.
- WEREN'T EXPECTING THAT,
WERE YOU?
- THEIR STRENGTH COMBINED
IS TERRIFYING.
- NOW FOR THE FINAL BLOW.
- YEP.  THAT FIRE IS
PRETTY HOT, ALL RIGHT.
- GRAY.
- HOO-HOO!  AND WHO ARE YOU?
- HEY YOU! I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA CATCH THAT SHO GUY
AND RESCUE ERZA.
- THAT'S WHERE I WAS HEADED
WHEN THIS THING SHOWED UP.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO MESS
WITH HIM.  WE GOTTA FIND HER.
BECAUSE IF WE DON'T,
THERE'S A CHANCE THAT SHE'LL
END UP AS JELLAL'S SACRIFICE.
- ( groans ) NORMALLY I'M SURE
SHE'D HAVE NO PROBLEM
TAKING HIM DOWN ON HER OWN,
BUT SHE'S HELPLESS
AS LONG AS THAT PSYCHO FRIEND
OF YOURS
HAS HER TRAPPED
INSIDE THAT CARD.
- I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT SHO
COULD HANDLE THE TRUTH.
I NEVER WOULD'VE IMAGINED
HE'D GO BERSERK LIKE THAT.
- GRAY, SAVE HIM.
HE NEEDS YOU.
- WHEN ARE YOU GONNA LEARN
TO STAY OUTTA TROUBLE?
THIS IS THE LAST TIME
I'M PUTTING MY NECK
ON THE LINE FOR YOU.
YOU HEAR?
- ( shouts )
- THE DIGESTION PROCESS
HAS BEGUN.
IN A MERE TEN MINUTES TIME,
SALAMANDER'S BODY WILL BE FULLY
DISSOLVED WITHIN MY OWN.
ONCE THAT HAPPENS, I'LL BE ABLE
TO USE HIS MAGIC POWERS
TO BRING YOU TO JUSTICE.
- OH, YEAH?
I WOULDN'T COUNT ON IT, BUDDY.
YOU'LL FALL TOO.
- ICE MAKE LANCE!
- FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- WATCH OUT!
HE'S TWICE AS STRONG NOW
THAT HE CAN USE
SALAMANDER'S POWERS.
- ( grunts )
- HOO HOO!
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT ICE
IS NO MATCH FOR FIRE.
- ( screaming )
- GRAY!
- IT'S NO USE.
YOUR FRIEND WAS EVEN STRONGER
THAN YOU REALIZED.
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIS FLAMES.
- ( cheering )
- ( laughing )
- I FEEL BAD FOR HER
'CAUSE SHE'S ALWAYS ALONE.
- DON'T JUST SIT THERE FEELING
SORRY FOR HER.  GO SAY HI.
- I TRIED THAT,
BUT SHE TOTALLY IGNORED ME.
- WELL, SHE SHOULD UNDERSTAND
BY NOW
THAT SHE'S NOT GONNA GET
ANYWHERE IN THIS GUILD
IF SHE DOESN'T WANNA TALK
TO THE GRAY.
- YOU ARE GETTING WAY TOO BIG
FOR YOUR BRITCHES THERE,
STREAKER.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- IS THERE A PROBLEM?
- YOU KNOW THIS IS A WIZARD'S
GUILD, RIGHT?
THAT STUPID ARMOR
WON'T PROTECT YOU HERE.
- MAYBE NOT BUT AT LEAST I HAVE
THE COMMON DECENCY
TO WEAR SOMETHING.  THAT'S MORE
THAN I CAN SAY FOR YOU, PERV.
- BE CAREFUL, GUYS.
LOOKS LIKE WE GOT A LIVE ONE.
- SHE SURE FIGURED YOU OUT
QUICK, GRAY.
- WHAT'D YOU CALL ME?
- IF YOU'RE SMART,
YOU'LL LEAVE ME ALONE.
- ( grunts )
- HE WAS ABLE
TO FREEZE THE FIRE.
- NATSU'S FLAMES ARE WAY HOTTER,
PAL, BUT I EXPECTED THAT
'CAUSE YOU'RE JUST SOME
BIRD-BRAINED POSER.
- HOO HOO! THAT'S SOME
IMPRESSIVE POWER YOU'VE GOT.
MAYBE I SHOULD CAPTURE YOU, TOO.
- GRAY!
- OH! TOO COLD!
- I'M NOT GONNA WASTE ANY MORE
OF MY TIME
PLAYING THESE STUPID GAMES
WITH YOU.
I'VE GOT MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
TO DO, LIKE RESCUE ERZA.
- DID YOU LET THAT LITTLE GIRL
BEAT THE CRAP OUT OF YOU AGAIN?
- YOU KNOW, I'M STARTING
TO THINK YOU LIKE IT.
OR MAYBE YOU JUST LIKE HER.
- OH, SHUT UP!
- SHE MUST BE PRETTY TOUGH IF
SHE CAN TAKE DOWN THE GRAY, HUH?
YEAH, IF SHE KEEPS IT UP,
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
SHE'LL BE CALLING THE SHOTS
AROUND HERE.
-NO, SHE WON'T.
SHE'LL NEVER BE ONE OF US.
ERZA, I SWEAR I'LL BRING YOU
BACK HOME.
- CAN'T HIDE FROM ME,
YOU RED-HEADED FREAK.
ALL RIGHT, ERZA, BRING IT ON.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S GOING DOWN
THIS TIME.
- IT'S YOU AGAIN.
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU?
HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED YOUR LESSON?
ALL RIGHT,
GIVE ME YOUR BEST SHOT.
- OH.  WELL, UH...
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?  YOU'RE NOT
CHICKENING OUT, ARE YOU?
- TELL ME SOMETHING.  HOW COME
YOU'RE ALONE ALL THE TIME?
- I JUST PREFER TO BE ALONE
'CAUSE I GET NERVOUS
AROUND OTHER PEOPLE.
- OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU'RE ALONE NOW,
SO WHY YOU CRYING?
- ( gasps )
SO YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
FIGHT ME TODAY?
- I CAN'T FIGHT A GIRL
WHO'S CRYING.
- ( shouting )
- OUT OF MY WAY.
ICE BLADE SEVEN STRIKE DANCE.
- OH!
- ( grunts )
- HE BEAT HIM!
- SHE KEPT HER HEART SHIELDED
IN ARMOR
BECAUSE SHE THOUGHT THAT WAS THE
ONLY WAY TO KEEP IT
FROM BREAKING AGAIN,
BUT IT DIDN'T STOP THE PAIN.
- NATSU.
- THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
- I HOPE SHE KNOWS HER FRIENDS
IN FAIRY TAIL
ARE TEN TIMES BETTER
THAN ANY ARMOR.
WITH US AROUND,
SHE'LL NEVER CRY AGAIN.
- THERE ARE NOW EIGHT VOTES
IN FAVOR AND ONLY ONE AGAINST.
THEREFORE, AN ETHERION BLAST
WILL BE USED
TO STRIKE DOWN THE TOWER
OF HEAVEN.
- THE COUNCIL'S MADE A DECISION.
- THE ETHERION WILL BE FIRED
IN ONE HOUR.
- BEGIN THE PREPARATIONS!
- ( clamoring )
- ( knock on door )
- ENTER.
- PLEASE FORGIVE MY INTRUSION.
- YAJIMA.
- I'M SORRY, SIEG,
BUT I DON'T THINK THIS
IS A WISE MOVE.
SURELY AN INTELLIGENT MAN
LIKE YOURSELF
COULD EASILY COME UP
WITH A MORE PEACEFUL WAY
OF RESOLVING THIS
VOLATILE SITUATION.
I WISH THERE WAS ANOTHER WAY,
BUT THE CONSEQUENCES
OF ZEREF'S RESURRECTION
ARE JUST TOO DIRE.
THAT'S WHY WE MUST STOP HIM
BY ANY MEANS NECESSARY.
YOU UNDERSTAND,
DON'T YOU, ELDER?
- ( sighs ) YES, WE MUST
STOP JELLAL, I AGREE.
BUT CAN YOU LIVE WITH THE
CONSEQUENCES OF TODAY'S VOTE?
- OF COURSE.  THAT'S A BURDEN
I'M WILLING TO BEAR.
- THIS BLAST COULD KILL
THOUSANDS OF INNOCENT PEOPLE,
INCLUDING YOUR
OWN TWIN BROTHER!
I HOPE YOU REALIZE THE BURDEN
OF HIS DEATH
AND THE COUNTLESS OTHERS
THAT FALL ALONGSIDE HIM
WILL REST SQUARELY
ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
DO YOU?
- I KNOW WHAT IS
AT STAKE HERE.
AND I'M PREPARED
TO DO WHAT I MUST.
SO YOUR MOVE NOW,
BUT YOU'D BETTER HURRY.
SOON THE LIGHT WILL RAIN DOWN
UPON OUR HEADS.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, WHAT THE HECK HAPPENED
TO MR. HOOTY-HOO ANYWAY?
- YOU MEAN THE OWL GUY?
GRAY TOOK CARE OF HIM
WHILE YOU WERE OUT COLD.
- AWW, MAN, THAT STINKS.
I HATE THAT STUPID
BOXER-SHORTS-WEARING JERK.
HOW COME HE'S ALWAYS
HOGGING ALL THE FUN?
THAT'S IT.
I DEMAND A REMATCH RIGHT NOW.
- COME ON, JUST LET IT GO.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO FIGHT HIM AGAIN.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- BESIDES,
JELLAL'S THE MAIN BADDIE.
BEATING HIM WILL BE WAY COOLER.
- YOU THINK SO?  SWEET!
THEN LET'S GO GET HIM.
CAN WE TAKE A BREAK FIRST?