- HEY, GUYS!  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Erza:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- CONSPIRING?
- NOT EXACTLY.
- Gray: WE FOUND OUT THAT
SIEGRAIN AND JELLAL
ARE THE SAME PERSON.
AND THE ETHERION WAS FIRED,
RELEASING A HUGE AMOUNT
OF MAGIC ENERGY THAT TRANSFORMED
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN
INTO ITS TRUE FORM.
- Natsu: AND WHEN SHE WAKES UP
FROM THIS NIGHTMARE,
I WANT HER TO FEEL
LIKE HER OLD SELF AGAIN.
TO GET TO HER,
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO THROUGH ME.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Lucy: YOU THINK NATSU AND ERZA
ARE OKAY IN THERE?
- Happy: THEY'RE GONNA BE FINE.
I KNOW IT.
THEY'RE TWO OF FAIRY TAIL'S
STRONGEST WIZARDS.
THEY CAN HANDLE THIS.
- Gray: HE'S RIGHT.
SINCE WE CAN'T HELP 'EM,
WE JUST GOTTA HAVE FAITH
THAT THEY'RE GONNA MAKE IT
OUT OF THIS.
- NOW I'M ALL FIRED UP,
EVEN MORE THAN
I'VE EVER BEEN BEFORE.
- I'M NOT GOING TO
LET YOU GET IN MY WAY.
THIS'LL BE THE END OF YOU.
I'VE DREAMED OF THIS DAY,
AND I WON'T LET A FOOL
LIKE YOU SPOIL IT FOR ME.
- SORRY, PAL,
BUT I'M A PRETTY TOUGH GUY.
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME
THEN COME AND GET ME.
TOO SLOW, HUH?
I GOT YOU NOW.
( Happy speaking )
- NATSU!
- ( screaming )
- HA HA! YOU'RE SO WORRIED ABOUT
WRECKING YOUR PRECIOUS TOWER,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
FIGHT ME FULL-ON?
'CAUSE I GET THE FEELING
YOU'RE HOLDING BACK.
AND THAT AIN'T GONNA WORK
AGAINST ME.
- I'D WATCH MY MOUTH
IF I WERE YOU.
- FIRE DRAGON BRILLIANT FLAME!
- HE'S AIMING FOR THE TOWER.
- NOW I'M ANGRY.
I DIDN'T SPEND YEARS BUILDING
THIS TOWER JUST
TO HAVE SOME PUNK
TEAR IT DOWN.
I WON'T LET YOU.
- ( laughs )
TOUGH BREAK, PAL, BUT YOU
CAN'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
I TOLD YOU DESTROYING STUFF
IS ONE OF MY SPECIALTIES.
- BE CAREFUL, NATSU.
YOU'RE WEAK.
YOU BARELY HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO STAND.
- I'LL MAKE YOU PAY!
- ( gasps )
- WHOA, SOMETHING WEIRD'S
GOING ON WITH HIS MAGIC.
IT'S MAKING ME FEEL SICK.
- WHY'S MY SHADOW BENDING
TOWARDS THE LIGHT?  THAT SPELL!
IT COULD KILL NATSU.
- AND NOW I'LL PLUNGE YOU
INTO INFINITE DARKNESS,
DRAGON SLAYER.
- Erza: DON'T DO IT.
UNLESS YOU WANT
TO KILL ME, TOO.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOUR
SACRIFICE TO ZEREF, DO YOU?
- THAT WOULD BE A PROBLEM.
THE CEREMONY REQUIRES THE BODY
OF A WIZARD
COMPARABLE IN STRENGTH TO ONE
OF THE TEN WIZARD SAINTS.
HOWEVER, I CAN FIND
A SUITABLE REPLACEMENT.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO FITS THAT BILL.
I'LL WORRY ABOUT THAT
AFTER I KILL BOTH OF YOU.
- WATCH OUT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- IT'S MY FAULT THAT YOU'RE
INVOLVED IN THIS MESS.
THE LEAST I CAN DO
IS PROTECT YOU.
- GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- HEAVENLY BODY MAGIC,
ALTAIRIS!
- Natsu: ERZA!
- ( grunting )
- WHOA, WHAT HAPPENED?
- THE TOP OF IT BLEW UP.
- BUT THEY'LL BE OKAY,
WON'T THEY?
- ( gasps )
- SHO, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I GOT A BAD FEELING JUST NOW.
- Natsu: IT'S YOU.
- WHY, SIMON?
- ( grunting )
TO SAVE YOU.
- SIMON!
- I HAD NO IDEA YOU WERE STILL
CRAWLING AROUND THE TOWER,
YOU DESPICABLE PEST.
- WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU THINKING?
WHY DIDN'T YOU ESCAPE
WITH THE OTHERS?
TALK TO ME!
- ( ragged breathing )
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M HAPPY
TO GIVE MY...
LIFE FOR YOU.
( coughs )
- SAVE YOUR ENERGY.
DON'T TALK ANYMORE.
JUST TRY TO STAY WITH ME.
- YOU WERE
THE ONLY PERSON
WHO MADE ME SMILE.
- DON'T DIE ON ME.
SIMON...  SIMON!
- I'VE ALWAYS
LOVED YOU.
- ( whimpering )
( crying )
NO!
- ( laughing )
WHAT A PERFECTLY
FOOLISH THING TO DO.
HE TRIED TO PLAY
THE VALIANT HERO,
BUT HIS DEATH WON'T
CHANGE A THING.
SIMON GAVE HIS OWN LIFE
TO SAVE YOURS,
BUT HE SHOULD HAVE KNOWN I'M
NOT LETTING EITHER OF YOU
LEAVE THIS TOWER ALIVE.
- SHUT UP!
- ( screams )
( grunting )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
HE'S EATING THE ETHER-NANO
FROM THE ETHERION BLAST.
- ( gulps )
( roaring )
( gagging )
- HOW COULD YOU BE SO STUPID?
ETHER-NANO IS MADE OUT
OF ALL TYPES OF ELEMENTAL MAGIC.
IT'LL POISON YOU.
- ( screaming )
- WHAT AN IDIOT.
DID HE REALLY THINK HE'D BE ABLE
TO POWER UP
BY CONSUMING ELEMENTS
OTHER THAN HIS OWN?
IT'LL CERTAINLY MAKE MY JOB
EASIER IF HE KILLS HIMSELF.
- ( screaming )
- NO.
- ( snarls )
- HIS BODY ABSORBED THE MAGIC
ENERGY FROM THE ETHER-NANO.
- YOU MADE ERZA CRY.
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
GET AWAY WITH THAT.
- ( screaming )
- I MADE A PROMISE
AND I'M NOT GONNA BREAK IT.
- NATSU, PROMISE YOU'LL
TAKE CARE OF HER.
- HURT HER AGAIN
AND I'LL KILL YOU!
- YOUR THREATS DON'T SCARE ME.
METEOR!
- ( gasps )
( screaming )
- YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO CATCH
ME AT THIS RATE OF SPEED.
I WON'T LOSE.
NOT TO YOU.
- UGH!
- I'M DESTINED TO CREATE
A LAND OF FREEDOM.
I KNOW BECAUSE
IN MY DARKEST HOUR,
I COULD HEAR LORD ZEREF
CALLING OUT TO ME.
HE TOLD ME HE COULD MAKE
ALL MY DREAMS COME TRUE,
AND I BELIEVE HIM.
THERE'S A REASON
I'M THE ONLY HUMAN
WHO CAN SENSE ZEREF'S PRESENCE.
IT'S BECAUSE
I AM THE CHOSEN ONE.
ONCE HE'S BEEN RESURRECTED,
WE'LL WORK TOGETHER
TO CREATE A LAND
THAT'S TRULY FREE.
- YOU'RE GONNA DO THAT
BY TAKING AWAY THE RIGHTS
OF EVERYONE ELSE IN THE WORLD?
- IF THAT'S WHAT HAS TO BE DONE
IN ORDER TO CHANGE THIS WORLD
INTO A BETTER PLACE,
THEN SO BE IT.
I COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHAT HAPPENS
TO FEEBLEMINDED
FOOLS LIKE YOU.
- HE'S CASTING THE ABYSS BREAK.
BUT WHY?
YOU'LL DESTROY THE TOWER
SO MANY DIED TO CREATE.
- THIS TOWER MEANS NOTHING.
YOU SEE, NOW THAT I'VE DONE IT,
I COULD BUILD ANOTHER
IN HALF THE TIME.
LORD ZEREF,
YOUR HOUR IS NEAR.
- YOU'LL NEVER KNOW WHAT
IT MEANS TO BE FREE.
NOT AS LONG AS YOU'RE POSSESSED
BY THAT SPIRIT.
WHY ARE YOU LETTING HIM
MANIPULATE YOU?
YOU CAN DO IT, JELLAL.
FREE YOURSELF!
- WHAT IN THE WORLD'S GOING ON?
- WAS THAT ANOTHER EXPLOSION?
- NO WAY.
THAT'S GOTTA BE NATSU.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.  HE MUST BE
UP THERE FIGHTING SOMEONE.
- OH, NO.  DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE GONNA BE OKAY?
- I SURE HOPE SO,
BUT IT'S STILL TOO SOON TO TELL,
'CAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S
GOING ON A MAJOR RAMPAGE.
- Erza: SO THIS IS THE POWER
THAT WAS HIDDEN WITHIN HIM.
THE TRUE FORM
OF THE DRAGON SLAYER.
HE WAS ABLE
TO DEFEAT JELLAL.
- ( laughs )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
THE NIGHTMARE IS OVER.
NOW SHO AND THE OTHERS
CAN FINALLY BE FREE.
NATSU!
I KNEW YOU'D FIND
YOUR INNER STRENGTH.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
- Millianna: SO PRETTY.
- Wally: THIS IS BAD NEWS.
- Juvia: THERE'S AN INCREDIBLE
AMOUNT OF MAGIC ENERGY
RESONATING FROM THAT LIGHT.
- Gray: THAT'S NOT A GOOD SIGN.
THE ETHER-NANO INSIDE THE TOWER
MUST BE GETTING OUT OF CONTROL.
- WHAT?  WHAT IS THAT?
- MAGIC ENERGY
FROM THE ETHERION.
- IT'S DANGEROUS FOR THAT MUCH
OF IT TO BE CONTAINED
IN ONE PLACE FOR TOO LONG 'CAUSE
THE ENERGY WILL KEEP BUILDING
TILL IT BECOMES UNSTABLE.
- WITH NOWHERE TO GO,
THE ETHER-NANO WILL KEEP GROWING
TILL IT BURSTS,
CAUSING A TREMENDOUS EXPLOSION.
- WHAT? WE'D BETTER START MAKING
TRACKS OR WE'RE DEAD MEAT.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT THE OTHERS
TRAPPED INSIDE?
- AT THIS POINT,
THERE'S NO SENSE IN WORRYING
ABOUT WHO'S GONNA MAKE IT OUT
OF THERE ALIVE AND WHO'S NOT.
'CAUSE IF THAT TOWER EXPLODES,
IT'LL WIPE US ALL OUT.
- GOODBYE.
UGH!
THE LACRIMA CAN'T CONTAIN
THIS MUCH MAGIC ENERGY.
IT'S TRANSFORMING.
I CAN'T IMAGINE HOW MUCH
DESTRUCTIVE POWER IT HAS.
EVEN IF WE MADE IT
OUTSIDE THE TOWER,
WE'D STILL BE CAUGHT
IN THE EXPLOSION.
NO, IT'S OVER.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
I CAN'T GIVE UP.
NATSU,
NOW IT'S MY TURN
TO SAVE YOU.
BUT IF THERE'S NO WAY TO CONTAIN
THE BLAST OR ESCAPE IT,
THEN WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
( gasps )
- THE MAGIC ENERGY HELD
WITHIN THIS LACRIMA
MUST NOW BE FUSED
WITH THE BODY OF MY SACRIFICE.
ONCE THAT HAPPENS, YOUR FLESH
WILL BEGIN TO BREAK DOWN
AND RECONSTRUCT ITSELF
INTO ZEREF'S BODY.
- THAT'S IT.
IF I FUSE MY BODY
WITH THE MAGIC ENERGY
INSIDE THE LACRIMA,
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO CONTROL IT
AND KEEP IT FROM EXPLODING.
IT'S A RISK
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE.
OH!  GOOD.
I WAS WORRIED THAT
IT MIGHT REJECT ME.
( grunting )
- ERZA.
- NATSU.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T GET IT.
ARE YOU TRYING TO GO BACK
INSIDE THAT THING?
- I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I'LL
EVER BE ABLE TO STOP IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
STOP WHAT?
- ( loud rumbling )
- NOW YOU SEE.
IT'S THE ETHER-NANO.
IF IT CONTINUES TO GAIN POWER,
THE LACRIMA WON'T BE ABLE
TO CONTAIN IT
AND THE WHOLE PLACE
WILL EXPLODE.
BUT IF I FUSE MY BODY
WITH THE MAGIC ENERGY,
I CAN PREVENT THAT
FROM HAPPENING.
- I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU DO THAT.
THERE'S GOTTA BE ANOTHER WAY
TO STOP IT.
- ( screaming )
- ERZA!
- I PROMISE I'LL STOP IT.
THERE'S NO NEED TO WORRY.
I'M DETERMINED
TO SAVE ALL OF YOU.
- NO!
- ( screaming )
- DON'T DO IT.
- I HAVE TO.
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE WHAT
MY LIFE WOULD'VE BEEN LIKE
WITHOUT FAIRY TAIL.
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR YOU AND THE OTHERS,
I PROBABLY WOULDN'T
BE HERE TODAY.
I HOPE YOU KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
YOU ALL ARE TO ME.
I CARE FOR YOU SO MUCH.
- ERZA.
- THAT'S WHY I'M WILLING TO MAKE
THE ULTIMATE SACRIFICE.
IF IT MEANS MY LOVED ONES
WILL BE SPARED,
I'LL GLADLY GIVE MY LIFE--
( shudders )
SO THAT YOU MAY LIVE.
- NO WAY!
COME OUT OF THERE RIGHT NOW.
- NATSU, PLEASE WATCH OVER
EVERYONE FOR ME.
- YOU CAN'T LEAVE US.  NO!
- I PROMISE YOU,
I'LL ALWAYS BE THERE
BY YOUR SIDE.
- ERZA!
- Wally: OH, CRAP!
IT'S EXPLODING.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK.
THE MAGIC ENERGY'S SHOOTING
UPWARDS OUT OF THE TOWER,
INTO THE SKY.
- ( gasps )
- ( all screaming )
- WHERE'D THE TOWER GO?
- IT WAS JUST THERE
A SECOND AGO.
- NATSU, WHERE ARE YOU?
- I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT HER EYE
WAS SO BADLY INJURED.
IT'LL BE NEXT TO IMPOSSIBLE
FOR ME
TO COMPLETELY RESTORE
HER SIGHT AGAIN.
- AWW, COME ON,
DON'T BE SO NEGATIVE.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.  IT'S JUST
A SHAME SHE HAS TO WEAR
THAT UGLY EYE PATCH WHEN SHE HAS
SUCH A PRETTY LITTLE FACE.
- ( gasps )
- MAKAROV.
- NO, NO, NOT THE EAR AGAIN.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I HATE THAT.
- YOU'RE NOT PLANNING ON PUTTING
THE MOVES ON HER
WHEN SHE GROWS UP, ARE YOU?
- NOT LITTLE OLD ME.
- SO WHAT'S HER STORY?
- SHE'S NOT MUCH OF A TALKER.
BUT APPARENTLY, ROB
SENT HER TO ME.
- OUR ROB?  WELL, DOES SHE
KNOW WHERE HE IS NOW?
- ACCORDING TO THE CHILD,
HE'S DEAD.
- ( gasps )
- TAKE A LOOK.
IT'S HEALED.
- YOU CAN SEE WITH IT?
- YES, MA'AM.
- THEN I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU LEAVE, YOUNG LADY.
NOTHING PERSONAL,
BUT I DON'T CARE MUCH
FOR PEOPLE.
- ( cries )
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- ( gasps ) WAIT A MINUTE.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
WHEN YOU CRY, THE INJURED EYE
ISN'T TEARING UP.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S WRONG.
I MIXED THE MEDICINAL COMPOUND
PERFECTLY.
WHAT COULD HAVE HAPPENED?
- IT'S OKAY, MA'AM.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IT'S PROBABLY 'CAUSE
I'VE CRIED SO MUCH,
I DON'T HAVE MANY TEARS LEFT.
- WHERE AM I?
- ( end theme playing )
- (singing in Japanese )
- YOU HEAR THE BIG NEWS?
THE NEW GUILD HALL'S FINISHED.
WE'LL BE BACK IN BUSINESS
IN NO TIME.
- THAT'S AWESOME.  I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE HOW THE PLACE TURNED OUT.
- NOW THAT IT'S BEEN REBUILT,
CAN YOU DO US ALL A FAVOR
AND TRY NOT TO GO DESTROYING IT?
- WHOA! C'MON, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
WHY YOU GOTTA ACT LIKE I'M
ALWAYS WRECKING EVERYTHING?
- HOLD UP.  ARE YOU MESSING
WITH ME?  YOU SAID IT YOURSELF.
- Natsu: I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE.
ERZA AND GRAY HAVE DONE THEIR
FAIR SHARE
OF MESSING STUFF UP, TOO.
- YEAH, BUT YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
ALWAYS STARTING THE FIGHTS.
- HOW COME I GET BLAMED
FOR EVERYTHING?