- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Happy: IT WAS TOUGH,
BUT OUR BAND OF HEROES
FINALLY BEAT THE ORACION SEIS
AND NIRVANA.
GO TEAM!
- Lucy: UNFORTUNATELY,
THE SWEET TASTE OF VICTORY
TURNED BITTER
AS WE WERE FORCED
TO SAY GOODBYE TO DEAR FRIENDS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ultear: MASTER HADES.
I'M SORRY TO DISTURB YOU,
MY LORD.
- Hades: IS IT AS I EXPECTED?
- IT IS INDEED, MASTER.
THE ORACION SEIS HAVE FALLEN
AND NIRVANA WAS DESTROYED
BY THE OFFICIAL GUILDS.
- THE COALITION WAS AS CAPABLE
AS I'D ANTICIPATED.
OUR OBJECTIVE
REMAINS UNHINDERED.
- YES, SIR. NIRVANA'S
DESTRUCTION IS BUT A RIPPLE
IN THE VAST SEA OF OUR SCHEME.
IT WON'T BE LONG
BEFORE WE POSSESS
THE KEYS TO ZEREF'S SEAL.
HOWEVER--
- DO NOT TRY MY
PATIENCE, ULTEAR.
- NIRVANA'S DESTRUCTION
MAY SERVE AS THE HERALD
OF AN EVEN
GREATER DISTURBANCE.
SO GREAT, IN FACT, THAT IT WILL
RENDER OUR GOALS UNREACHABLE
IF LEFT UNCHECKED.
- ( chuckles )
NOW THIS IS ENTERTAINING.
YOU AREN'T AFRAID, ARE YOU?
- NOT AT ALL,
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
- AH! SO THIS IS WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO SAIL THE SEAS
WITHOUT PUKING
YOUR BRAINS OUT.
- AYE, MATEY,
WELCOME TO THE GOOD LIFE.
- HA HA!
LOOK OUT, VEHICLES.
NATSU'S GONNA RIDE YOU HARD.
- CAREFUL!
THE TROIA SPELL
DOESN'T LAST FOREVER.
- FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO MIGHT NOT KNOW,
TROIA IS A HEALING SPELL
THAT CURES MOTION SICKNESS.
- ARGH! NO.
CAST THAT SPELL AGAIN.
HURRY.
- I'M SORRY, I CAN'T.
IT ONLY WORKS
A COUPLE OF TIMES.
- GUESS IT'S BACK TO BARF BAGS.
- ( laughs )
- WHEN YOU AND WENDY
JOIN FAIRY TAIL,
I'LL SHOW YOU ALL THE SNUGGLING
SPOTS PERFECT FOR KITTIES.
- I'M JOINING YOUR GUILD
TO STAY CLOSE TO WENDY,
NOT BECAUSE I HAVE ANY INTEREST
IN YOU.
- WE'RE JOINING FAIRY TAIL!
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
- ( Happy speaking )
- Lucy: WITH A HARD-FOUGHT
BATTLE NOW BEHIND US,
IT'S FINALLY TIME
TO RETURN TO HOME.
- MAN!  MAY YOUR PARFUMS
GRACE MY NOSTRILS AGAIN,
MISS ERZA AND MISS LUCY.
- BE SURE TO COME VISIT US
WHENEVER YOU FEEL LIKE IT.
- WHEN YOU DO, BE READY
FOR THE BEST NIGHT
BLUE PEGASUS CAN OFFER.
- GIVE MY WARMEST REGARDS
TO MASTER MAKAROV.
- OH, AND GRAY,
FIX THAT STRIPPING HABIT.
- LIKE YOU HAVE
ANY ROOM TO TALK, YOU BONEHEAD!
- QUESTION.
WHAT DO WE DO
ABOUT THOSE TWO?
- WELL, AREN'T YOU RUNNING
OFF WITH YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS?
- YEAH, AND JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT GONNA MISS YOU.
- SHERRY.
- REN.
- THEY'RE SO IN LOVE!
- Lucy: IT'S CERTAINLY BEEN
A WILD RIDE, MOM.
OH, AND YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT HAPPENED.
I GOT
THREE NEW CELESTIAL KEYS.
- Gemi: ANGEL'S LOCKED UP,
SO NOW OUR CONTRACTS WITH HER
ARE NULL AND VOID.
- Mini: THAT'S RIGHT.
- NOW THAT WE'RE FREE.
WE'VE ALL DECIDED
THE BEST PERSON
TO TAKE OVER OUR CONTRACTS
WOULD BE NONE OTHER THAN YOU,
LUCY HEARTFILIA.
WICKED!
- WOULD YOU PLEASE BE OUR
WIZARD? - Both: PIRI-PIRI.
- SO YOU REALLY WANT
TO FORM CONTRACTS WITH ME?
ARE YOU GUYS SURE ABOUT THIS?
YOU "GUYS"?
- WE'RE JUST USED
TO BEING CALLED PETS
AFTER WORKING WITH ANGEL
ALL THIS TIME.
- I KNOW.
BUT THAT DOESN'T WORK FOR ME.
I THINK
OF MY SPIRITS AS EQUALS.
YOU'RE NO DIFFERENT TO ME
THAN MY GUILD MATES.
YOU'RE LIKE FAMILY.
- HMMM!
- IT WOULD BE OUR PLEASURE
TO WORK WITH YOU, LUCY.
- Both: PIRI-PIRI.
- I HOPE WE'RE TOGETHER
FOR A LONG TIME,
SCORPIO, GEMINI AND ARIES.
NEW FRIENDS ARE COMING
INTO MY LIFE IN DROVES.
AND I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER!
- Erza: LONG STORY SHORT--
WENDY AND CARLA ARE
FAIRY TAIL'S NEWEST MEMBERS,
SO YOU'D BETTER
TREAT THEM WELL.
- IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU ALL.
- ADORABLE! - LOOK
THERE'S EVEN A FEMALE HAPPY.
- I BET YOUR MOM'S
REAL PRETTY!
- WE'RE SO GLAD YOU MADE IT
BACK SAFELY.
- HELLO, MASTER.
- GREAT WORK, ERZA.
I'M SURE THINGS
WILL QUIET DOWN
NOW THAT THE ORACION SEIS
ARE OUT OF THE PICTURE.
AND THANKS FOR BRINGING
TWO PRECIOUS
YET POWERFUL ADDITIONS
TO THE GUILD BACK WITH YOU.
- GIRL,
IT'S BEEN TOO LONG!
- YOU'RE TELLING ME.
- HUG ATTACK!
- AWW.  NOW THAT'S AN ATTACK
I'LL ALWAYS TAKE.
- DOES LUCY
SEEM DIFFERENT TO YOU?
- KIND OF.
WHO KNOWS WHAT CRAZINESS
SHE HAD TO GO THROUGH?
- ( crashing )
- Both: OH!
- GRAY, DARLING.
YOU'RE BACK!
I'M SO HAPPY
YOU MADE IT HOME.
MY TEARS ARE FLOWING
LIKE WATERFALLS!
- GRAY. STOP YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
MAN, WE'RE DYING HERE!
- SHE'S NOT
MY FREAKIN' GIRLFRIEND!
- AND THEN THE GIANT SNAKE
SPROUTED WINGS
AND STARTED FLYING!
- YEAH, YEAH, NOW I KNOW
YOU'RE PULLING MY LEG.
SNAKES AREN'T MANLY ENOUGH
TO FLY.
- YOU SAW IT.
- WELCOME TO FAIRY TAIL,
YOU TWO.
I'M MIRAJANE.
- WOW!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
FIRST I MET ERZA,
NOW MISS MIRAJANE.
- I'M GUESSING YOUR FELINE
FRIEND USES
THE SAME MAGIC AS HAPPY.
YOU MIND TELLING US
WHAT TYPE OF MAGIC YOU USE?
- WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T YOU DARE COMPARE ME
TO THAT FURRY HORN DOG!
- DON'T MIND HER.
I USE HEALING
AND SUPPORT MAGIC.
ACTUALLY,
I'M A SKY DRAGON SLAYER.
- ( all gasping )
- DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG
ALREADY?
- All: THAT'S AWESOME!
WE HAVE
ANOTHER DRAGON SLAYER!
- AW, YEAH!
- JUST LIKE NATSU AND GAJEEL!
- I'VE NEVER HEARD OF A GUILD
WITH THREE DRAGON SLAYERS IN IT!
WE'RE GONNA BE
EVEN MORE UNSTOPPABLE NOW.
- WELCOME TO THE FAMILY.
HAPPY TO HAVE YOU ABOARD.
- ( both meowing )
- IT'S NOT FAIR.
SERIOUSLY!
I MEAN
I'M A DRAGON SLAYER TOO.
WHEN DO I GET
MY OWN FLYING KITTY CAT, HUH?
- ALL RIGHT EVERYONE,
LISTEN UP!
LET'S WELCOME OUR NEW MEMBERS
THE WAY ONLY FAIRY TAIL CAN!
NOW, EAT, DRINK,
AND MAKE MERRY!
YEAH!
WHO WANTS TO BRAWL?
- AH!  LOOK AT ME
AND YOU LOSE AN EYE.
OH YEAH?
WELL, IT'D BE WORTH IT, BABY.
- DARLING, ARE YOU CHEATING
ON ME WITH THAT TRAMP?
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
- YOU KNOW, CARLA, IF YOU EAT
A FISH WITH A LOVED ONE,
YOU'LL HAVE GOOD LUCK.
- THAT IS NOT YOU.
- EVERYONE IS SO LIVELY
AND FILLED WITH HAPPINESS.
- KEEP YOUR GUARD UP, CHILD.
- MMM.
- HAS ANYTHING ON THE BOARD
CAUGHT YOUR INTEREST?
- THERE'RE SO MANY,
IT'S HARD TO PICK ONE.
- TAKE YOUR TIME.
THOUGH, IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND
A LITTLE ADVICE,
I'D STAY AWAY
FROM SOLO JOBS FOR NOW.
SINCE YOU'RE
JUST STARTING OUT,
IT MIGHT BE BEST TO ASSIST
ANOTHER TEAM
WITH ONE OF THEIR JOBS.
- YOU'LL TAKE A PAY CUT,
OF COURSE,
BUT THE EXPERIENCE
IS WELL WORTH IT.
- SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
- I ADMIRE YOUR ENTHUSIASM,
BUT TAKE A LOOK
AT YOUR POTENTIAL PARTNERS.
- ( both laughing )
- ( squealing )
- NOT A CHANCE.
- HELPING WENDY FIND A GOOD JOB,
MIRAJANE?
- ACTUALLY, I THINK IT'D BE
BEST FOR HER TO TAG ALONG
ON SOMEONE ELSE'S JOB
AND GET SOME EXPERIENCE.
- GOOD PLAN.  I MEAN, LU-LU HERE
GOT HER START IN FAIRY TAIL
BY HELPING NATSU, RIGHT?
- AND IT'S LED ME INTO MORE
HORRIFYING AND DEADLY SITUATIONS
THAN ANY GIRL
SHOULD HAVE TO ENDURE.
- YOU'VE GOT MORE COURAGE
THAN ME, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- COURAGE.
WELL, THEN,
SINCE THE TWO OF YOU ARE HERE,
IS THERE ANY WORK
THAT YOU NEED HELP WITH?
I MAY STILL BE PRETTY GREEN,
BUT I PROMISE
TO DO MY VERY BEST.
- WE COULD REALLY USE THAT KIND
OF ATTITUDE IN SHADOW GEAR.
- YOU WORKED WITH US BEFORE,
SO WHY NOT STICK AROUND?
- UHH, SOMEHOW I THINK STICKING
WITH YOUR LITTLE GANG
MIGHT BE BAD FOR HER HEALTH.
- ( laughs )
- WHY NOT HAVE HER WORK
WITH BOTH TEAMS?
- GOOD IDEA.
- SO WHICH TEAM
GETS YA FIRST?
- HMM.
- YO, NATSU.
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- Elfman:
WHERE'VE YOU BEEN HIDING, MAN?
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU FOR DAYS.
DID YOU TAKE A VACATION?
- WHAT'S WRONG, MY LOVE?
YOU SEEM RATHER TROUBLED.
- WHEN I WAS ON MY WAY HERE
I HEARD SOMETHING CRAZY.
- AND THAT WOULD BE?
- THE RUMOR MILL'S RUNNING
PRETTY HARDCORE AROUND TOWN.
APPARENTLY THERE'S BEEN
A DRAGON SIGHTING.
- Happy: SOMEONE SAW A DRAGON?
FOR REAL?
- OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT MY ATTENTION.
WAS IT IGNEEL?
- I DIDN'T HEAR ANY NAMES,
SPECIFICALLY.
- ALL RIGHT. DID YOU
AT LEAST TALK TO THE GUY
WHO SAID HE SAW THIS DRAGON?
- NO.
LIKE I SAID,
IT'S JUST A RUMOR I HEARD.
APPARENTLY THE PERSON
WHO STARTED IT,
SOME WOMAN NAMED DAPHNE,
SAYS THERE'S MORE TO THE STORY.
ACCORDING TO HER,
SHE DIDN'T JUST SEE IT.
SHE SAYS SHE ACTUALLY SPOKE
WITH THE DRAGON.
- LIKE, IN PERSON?
IS IT TRUE, GRAY?
- DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S WORTH
CHECKING OUT, DON'T YA THINK?
- HOW DO WE FIND HER?
- GO TO THE RISE LODGE.
IT'S IN
THE WESTERN WASTELANDS.
- THANKS, I OWE YA ONE.
LET'S GO, HAPPY.
- AYE, SIR.
- MIND IF I COME?
I WON'T BUG YOU.
I JUST WANNA SEE
IF IT'S GRANDEENA.
- SURE, THE MORE THE MERRIER.
TAGGING' ALONG, GAJEEL?
- RUN AROUND WITH YOU LOSERS?
YEAH, LIKE I'D WANNA DO THAT.
- I KNOW YOU'RE AS CURIOUS
AS WE ARE.
- LISTEN TO YOURSELF
FOR TWO SECONDS.
YOU HEAR "DRAGON" AND YOU'RE OFF
ON A WILD GOOSE CHASE.
STORIES LIKE THIS
ARE SUCKERBAIT,
BUT I GUESS THEY HOOKED ONE.
IT'S POINTLESS
TO GET YOUR HOPES UP.
I LEARNED THAT
A LONG TIME AGO.
- WHAT IF IT WAS METALICANA?
WOULD YOU STILL
JUST SIT HERE?
- NO, I'D GO PUNCH HIM
IN THE FACE.
I DON'T GET WHY YOU'D CARE
ABOUT SOMEONE WHO ABANDONED YOU.
YOU WANNA WASTE TIME,
BE MY GUEST.
- YOU REALLY FEEL THAT WAY?
- I BET IF IT
REALLY WAS METALICANA,
HE'D GO RUNNING TO HIM
IN TEARS.
- DON'T LET HIM HEAR YOU
SAY THAT.
- GUESS IT'S JUST US THEN.
- RIGHT!
I HOPE IT REALLY IS GRANDEENA.
I MISS HER.
- I'M SURE.
BUT DON'T GET YOUR HOPES
TOO HIGH
OR YOU MIGHT BE DISAPPOINTED.
- THANKS FOR THE TIP, MAN.
I GUESS YOU REALLY
ARE USEFUL FOR SOMETHIN'.
- MY PLEASURE.
- Erza: I'D LIKE TO ORDER
THIS ONE.
- SURE.
I MUST SAY,
YOU'RE ONE OF MY MOST LOYAL
AND FREQUENT CUSTOMERS.
- I BUY ONE EACH TIME
WE RECRUIT NEW MEMBERS.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
IT'S TRADITION NOW.
- HEE HEE! HAPPY TO KNOW
THAT MY TREATS ARE APPRECIATED.
- YOU'RE A MASTER OF YOUR CRAFT.
SO ARE 50 CAKES DOABLE?
- EH?  YOU'VE RECRUITED
50 NEW MEMBERS?
- ONLY TWO, ACTUALLY.
THE REST ARE FOR ME.
- AHHH!
PLEASE, COME AGAIN!
- RE-QUIPPING?
I DON'T SENSE IT ANYMORE.
WHAT WAS THAT?
- Happy:
KIND LOOKS OUT OF PLACE, HUH?
- NOT TO MENTION RUN-DOWN.
- IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE ANYONE'S AROUND.
- I THINK THAT'S BY DESIGN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THIS PLACE IS RUN
AUTOMATICALLY
BY A LACRIMA LODGING SYSTEM.
IT CAN CHECK IN
AND CHECK OUT PATRONS,
SO THERE'S NO NEED TO HIRE
EMPLOYEES TO WORK THE DESK.
- WOW. BLESSED WITH BEAUTY
AND BRAINS TO BOOT.
- YOU'D THINK THERE'D AT
LEAST BE SOMEONE AROUND
TO MAINTAIN THE PLACE,
BUT I DON'T EVEN SEE
ANY LODGERS.
- NEXT TIME I SEE GRAY,
I'LL PUNCH HIM IN THE NOSE.
- IF YOU DON'T MIND
ME SAYING SO,
I THINK WE'RE JUMPING THE GUN.
THERE'RE PLENTY OF ROOMS
TO CHECK.
IF THE LODGE IS AUTOMATIC,
DAPHNE MIGHT BE STAYING
IN ONE OF THEM.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
LET'S SPLIT UP
AND START KNOCKING
ON ALL THE DOORS.
HELLO?
- SORRY TO DISTURB YOU.
- WOW!
YOU SAW NOTHING.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY, BABY.
- HONESTLY.
WHAT IS WITH
THIS SHODDY ROACH MOTEL?
- SO FAR WE'VE CHECKED OUT
ALMOST EVERY SINGLE ROOM
IN THIS PLACE.
- GUESS THAT MEANS
THIS IS THE LAST ONE--
WHICH IS SO NOT SUSPICIOUS
IN ANY WAY!
I MEAN, COME ON,
IS THAT A GIANT HAPPY DOLL?
IS ANYONE NAMED DAPHNE
IN THERE?!
- Daphne: YES YES!
- ALL RIGHT.
- OPEN UP.
WE NEED TO TALK WITH HER NOW!
- MY MY.
YOU CERTAINLY
ARE A NOISY BUNCH, AIN'T YA?
- WE HEARD YOU MIGHT
BE ABLE TO HELP US.
- OH, YES YES, INDEED!
HELPING'S WHAT I DO.
LOOK NO FURTHER, STRANGER,
YOUR SEARCH FOR AID IS OVER.
COME INSIDE
AND I'LL EASE YOUR BURDENS!
YES YES.
COME COME.
- Carla: WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- YOU'RE IN FOR A TREAT,
YES YES!
I'M A MISSIONARY OF BEAUTY
WHO TRAVELS THE LANDS,
AIDING FOLKS JUST LIKE YOU.
DAZZLIN' DAPHNE!
AND I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
THE OLD RUN-OF-THE-MILL
BEAUTY, FRIENDS.
I MEAN REAL BEAUTY.
GENUINE BEAUTY.
BEAUTIFUL BEAUTY
ONLY NATURE PROVIDES.
YES. YES. YES. YES.
AND HERE IS A FABULOUS PRODUCT
THAT WILL HELP YOU
ACHIEVE THE NATURAL MAGNIFICENCE
OF THE REDDEST ROSE.
MIRACLE DIET METAMO-CHAN.
- MULTIPLE CHINS?
- Fat Happy: YUMMY.
- BEAUTY, HUH?
- YES YES.
YOU! PLEASE DO NOT MISPRONOUNCE
THE NAME OF MY MONEY MAKER.
METAMO-CHAN FIGHTS OBESITY
WITH EASE.
ITS SCIENTIFICALLY CREATED,
NATURAL MONOUNSATURATED
AND POLYUNSATURATED NUTRIENTS
MELT THE POUNDS AWAY.
- EXCUSE ME.
- EVEN ITS CREATION IS A
DELICATE PROCESS.
FOR THREE WHOLE DAYS,
WE SOAK IT
IN A SECRET HERBAL SOLVENT,
AND THEN SUN-DRY IT FOR A WEEK
SO IT'S BURSTING WITH FLAVOR.
AND THE RESULT IS--
SAY IT RIGHT!
- THE MIRACULOUS DIET FOOD
METAMO-CHAN, MA'AM.
- GOOD GOOD.  SUPER JOB,
MY BABY BLUE FELINE FRIEND.
IN FACT, YOU DID SO GOOD
I'M GIVING YOU A SAMPLE,
COMPLETELY FREE. - BUT I'M NOT
OBESE, AND I ONLY EAT FISH--
YES, YES.  IT HAPPENS TO COME
IN FISH FLAVOR.
TAKE ONE BITE AND YOUR SKIN
WILL BE SILKY SMOOTH.
TAKE TWO BITES
AND YOU'LL BE AS SLIM AS ME.
AND YOU MUST BE HIS BROTHER
AND SISTERS. RIGHT RIGHT.
HAVE SOME FOR YOURSELVES,
ON THE HOUSE.
TAKE THE PLUNGE AND LIVE
THE DREAM OF ABSOLUTE BEAUTY.
DON'T BELIEVE ME?
SEE THE RESULTS FOR YOURSELF.
IT'S A MIRACLE.
- All: AMAZING!  WOW!
- I WANNA TRY SOME.
- WHAT?  WAIT.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
BUYING INTO THIS?
- IF YOU'RE STILL NOT CONVINCED
THIS IS RIGHT FOR YOU,
LISTEN TO REAL TESTIMONIALS
FROM REAL CUSTOMERS.
"METAMO-CHAN HAS
COMPLETELY TRANSFORMED ME,
JUST LIKE YOU SAID IT WOULD."
- WAIT A MINUTE.
- "10 DAYS LATER, AND I AM SLIM
AND GORGEOUS." - STOP TALKING.
- "DIET SPELLS ARE OUT FOR ME,
IT'S METAMO-CHAN OR BUST."
- YES YES, AND THE SUCCESS
LETTERS KEEP POURING IN
FROM ALL OVER FIORE
AND THE FAR REACHES OF THE WOR--
- QUIT SAYING "YES YES"!
- YES YES, OF COURSE, SIR.
YOU INTERESTED IN SIGNING UP FOR
THE "I BEAT OBESITY" NEWSLETTER?
- NO NO! I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN YOUR DUMB LETTERS,
YOUR OBESITY
OR YOUR FISHY DIET KABOB.
- A KABOB
SOUNDS LIKE A SUPER IDEA.
YOU WANT TO
BECOME BUSINESS PARTNERS?
- I'M ONLY INTERESTED
IN DRAGONS.
- YES YES,
EVERYONE HAS A PREFERENCE.
YOU WON'T FIND JUDGMENT HERE.
HOW MANY POUNDS DOES YOUR
"DRAGON" FRIEND WANNA SHED?
WE COULD WORK OUT
A DIET PLAN.
- WILL YOU SHUT YOUR MOUTH
FOR FIVE SECONDS?!
I'M A DRAGON SLAYER
FROM FAIRY TAIL.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR A DRAGON
NAMED IGNEEL WHO DISAPPEARED.
MY FRIEND HERE HAS ALSO BEEN
SEARCHING FOR ONE TOO--
THE SKY DRAGON, GRANDEENA.
WE HEARD A RUMOR
THAT YOU RECENTLY MET ONE.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
WE'RE HERE, ALL RIGHT?
SO IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING,
TELL US WHAT IT IS.
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
- HMM. STRANGE THAT HE
WOULD ATTACK THEN RETREAT.
- HE WAS LETTING ME KNOW
THAT HE'S OUT THERE
AND CAN ATTACK US
WHENEVER HE CHOOSES.
ALSO THERE WAS SOMETHING ODD
ABOUT HIM.
THE ONLY WAY I CAN PUT IT
IS THAT HE SMELLED WRONG.
- SMELLED WRONG?
- NOT LIKE A PERSON,
MORE LIKE A WILD ANIMAL.
EVEN THE WAY HE BREATHED
WAS UNNATURAL.
- SOUNDS TO ME LIKE ANOTHER
DARK GUILD OUT THERE
NEEDS A MANLY KICK
IN THE PANTS.
- WE'LL BE CAUTIOUS,
BUT NOT OVERLY SO.
I'M SURE
WE'LL SEE HIM AGAIN.
- ARE WE TO JUST SIT BACK
AND DO NOTHING THEN?
- THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT WE'LL DO FOR NOW.
WE'D WASTE RESOURCES OTHERWISE.
PROCEED AS IF NOTHING
HAS HAPPENED.
THAT SHOULD PROVOKE HIM
INTO REVEALING HIMSELF
SOONER RATHER THAN LATER.
- RIGHT.
- DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL PAY THIS GUY BACK,
PLUS INTEREST.
GRAY AND I ARE WITH YOU.
WHAT THE HECK?
WHERE'D HE GO?
- MY BELOVED HAS RUN OFF
WITHOUT TELLING ME
WHERE HE'S GONE
OR WHAT HE'S DOING.
DOESN'T HE CARE ABOUT MY
FEELINGS? - ON A JOB?!
- I DON'T KNOW!
- ( bird squawking )
- YES YES, I DID SAY
THAT I MET WITH A DRAGON.
BUT THAT WAS A JUST A FIB
FOR MARKETING.
SORRY.
- YOU LIED?
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
- AND THE WINNER IS GAJEEL!
- I HAD A FEELING THIS
WOULD JUST BE A WASTE OF TIME.
- YES YES.
METAMO-CHAN WORKS SO WELL
'CAUSE OF
THE PRIMARY INGREDIENT,
WHICH HAPPENS TO BE
POWDERED DRAGON SCALES.
WITHOUT 'EM, IT WOULD BE A
COMPLETE FLOP. - DRAGON SCALES?
- YES YES, INDEED.
OF COURSE, THAT'S A LIE TOO.
THOSE ARE IMPOSSIBLE
TO OBTAIN.
- YOU MEAN METAMO-CHAN
DOESN'T WORK?
- BINGO, DARLIN'!
A WELL-CRAFTED SCAM,
IF I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
- UNBELIEVABLE.
SHAMELESS!
- YES YES.  A GIRL'S GOTTA
MAKE A LIVING SOMEHOW.
I'M SURE YOU UNDERSTAND,
DRAGON BOY.
- I UNDERSTAND YOU SUCK!
WE'RE LEAVING.
AH!
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
- WHY IS THE HALLWAY MELTING?!
- HOW DOES
A WHOLE BUILDING VANISH?
- YOU'RE ALL MINE NOW,
BIRDS IN A CAGE.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
- OH NO!
- NATSU, ARE YOU OKAY?
- IT'S SOME KIND OF MAGIC WALL.
YOU'RE REALLY A WIZARD,
AREN'T YOU?
- ( laughs )
YES YES.
QUITE A DISPLAY, SALAMANDER.
IF ANYTHING, YOU LIVE UP
TO YOUR REPUTATION.
- SHE'S KIND OF SCARY
WITHOUT HER TWANG.
- I'M SO GLAD THAT ALL OF YOU
COULD MAKE IT.
GOOD THINGS REALLY DO COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
- THIS WAS JUST A SET-UP.
- YES YES YES!
AND YOU FELL RIGHT IN IT!
SO SIT BACK AND HAVE SOME
METAMO-CHAN.
- WHY WOULD I WANT THAT?
- PERHAPS YOU'D LIKE
THE STRAWBERRY FLAVOR?
- THERE'S ALSO WASABI
AND TERIYAKI. - I SAID NO!
- WE CAN'T GO OUT HERE EITHER.
- SEEMS THIS TRAP
WAS MASTERFULLY CRAFTED.
- YES YES YES.
MY MAGIC IS QUITE SPLENDID.
- I'VE NEVER MET A WALL
I COULDN'T BRING DOWN BY FORCE.
AHHH!
- AH!  NATSU!
- WHAT THE--
- HOW'S THE FLOOR FEEL,
NATSU?
- OH, IT'S GRAY!
- WAIT.
HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO GET PAST
THAT MAGIC WALL?
- GOOD QUESTION.
AND I'VE GOT MY OWN BONE
TO PICK WITH YOU.
NEXT TIME MAKE SURE YOUR INFO
ISN'T COMPLETE GARBAGE.
- HMMM.
IT WASN'T GARBAGE.
YOU DID JUST WE WANTED.
- YES YES YES, THEY DID.
SO GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT,
MY BELOVED GRAY.
- YOU KNOW HER?
WHAT IS GOING ON, MAN?
- ( laughs )
- WHOA!
I THINK THEY'RE IN LOVE!
- YOU'RE REALLY SLUMMIN' IT
IF YOU'RE WITH THIS CHICK.
- SHUT UP.
IF YOU DIDN'T THINK
THIS WAS GONNA HAPPEN ONE DAY,
YOU'RE EVEN DUMBER THAN I
THOUGHT. - WHAT WAS THAT?
- IT'S TIME FOR YOU AND ME
TO SETTLE THIS LITTLE RIVALRY
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
- JEEZ, YOU'RE SLOW.
I'M SAYIN' I'M TIRED
OF ALWAYS FOLLOWING YOUR LEAD.
NOW I'LL FOLLOW
MY OWN PATH.
AS OF THIS MOMENT,
I'M THROUGH WITH FAIRY TAIL.
AND I'M THROUGH
WITH ALL OF YOU.
- YOU'RE SERIOUS?
- YES YES.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL A MAN.
MY DARLING ICE-CUBE REALLY KNOWS
HOW TO WARM ME UP.
NOW BE A DEAR AND FETCH ME
A DRAGON SLAYER,
WOULD YOU?
- YOU DON'T WANT TO DO THIS,
GRAY.
- IF YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT,
STAY THERE.
IT'LL BE MUCH EASIER
TO END YOU!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: WHO DO YOU THINK
WOULD WIN IN A FIGHT?
- YOU OR GRAY?
- Natsu: ME, OF COURSE.
THERE'S NO WAY
SIR STRIPS-A-LOT'S
GONNA BRING ME DOWN.
- REALLY? 'CAUSE HE JUST
SAID, "THERE'S NO WAY
THAT PINK-HAIRED FLAME MUNCHER
WILL EVER BEAT ME."
- SAY WHAT? IT'S NOT PINK,
IT'S LIGHTISH RED.
THAT NO GOOD, BOXER DROPPING,
POPSICLE SHOVING, FREAK SHOW!
- IT'S NOT AN INSULT CONTEST.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: THE SIZE OF THE INSULT
DOESN'T MATTER.
REMEMBER,
BREVITY IS THE SOUL OF WIT.
- Natsu: HE STINKS!
- WELL, I GUESS IT WAS
PRETTY BRIEF, AT LEAST.