This doesn't make sense!
Natsu just closed Loke's gate!
So how is the
Liberam still going?
This won't end well.
[OPHIUCHUS] Omnia...
magna... stella... rex... prae.
Why is the snake chick
beltin' out a tune?
Can you tell
what she's saying?
"Omelet, mackerel, and
some shellfish tempura to go".
It's still not the time
to think with your stomach!
It's never the
right time with you.
She's saying,
"Omnia magna stella rex prae."
"All for the sake
of the King of stars."
It can't be!
You're out of
your depth, humans.
Don't interfere!
The time is nigh.
I can feel it!
You won't be
waiting long, my king.
[NATSU groaning in pain]
That was hard to watch, man.
Wasn't easy to do, either.
Also, you kinda look
like you're dying.
Oh yeah?
Well I've been feelin' like a
train-wreck for a while now.
My goodness!
What's wrong with you?
You're a little
off color, Natsu.
What?
Whoa, man!
You're sweatin' out party fog!
Is that bad?
My paw's melting!
I've never seen
a fever like this!
So did you catch a bug, then?
[NATSU]
Heck no. I don't get sick!
If you ate more fish,
you'd have a
stronger immune system.
It's not like that!
I've been feelin' weird
ever since I beat Loke.
Chances are it's got
somethin' to do with him.
[HAPPY]
Ophiuchus, the Snake Charmer!
[GRAY] So, we got
a destination, or...?
[ERZA] Hmm...
[GAJEEL] I'm catchin' a faint
whiff of Salamander
from over there.
[OPHIUCHUS] There's
nothing you can do now
but watch and weep,
you pathetic humans!
Anyone else hear
that sinister voice?
Yeah, it was like
it came out of nowhere.
Didn't sound like
any spirits I know of.
There is one other spirit
that should be around here.
Isn't there a
13th zodiac member?
That's the rumor anyway.
[OPHIUCHUS] Omnia...
magna... stella... rex... prae.
What was that?
I dunno, but it was creepy.
It sounded like
an incantation.
The Liberam?
It shan't be long now, comrades.
Very soon,
the shackles that bind you
to this earthly plane
will be severed!
Your liberation
is close at hand!
We're right in front
of her, ready to fight,
and she's actin'
like she already won!
Aw, man.
And this headache is killing me.
From the amount of
heat you're putting out,
I don't think that this
is an ordinary sickness.
It could be a side-effect
of Loke's darkness magic.
Say what?
[CARLA] You ate it, remember?
[WENDY] In that case...
My guess is that
darkness magic and dragon
slayer magic don't mix.
They're probably fighting
it out inside you as we speak.
It's kinda like
ya ate a chili-dog
right after downin'
some mint ice cream.
Except my stomach
isn't the problem!
Whatever this is,
I can't fight at full
strength until I get rid of it.
You've obviously been
weakened by the Liberam.
You can't win like this,
and I never wanted to fight you,
so let's stop!
I'm just getting started.
Yeah, well I'm about finished!
Let me go!
[LUCY] Not until I'm through!
I have something to tell you.
For the last time,
I don't care if
I die as long as I'm free!
That's not it!
This is about me and you, okay?
I'm not trying to
suppress a revolt here.
I'm just scared.
Scared of losing my friends.
Our bond wasn't about mastery.
We cared for each other.
Sure, it's a little
weird that you're always
asking about punishments and
calling me princess,
but that's okay,
because it's part of
what makes you who you are!
Pretty words
won't change my mind.
These are more
than just words!
Virgo, please look into my eyes.
You, Loke, Aquarius,
and all the other spirits
have shaped me into the
person that you're looking at.
The celestial spirits
I'm contracted to
are not my servants.
They are my life!
[yells]
No matter what you do,
we will complete the Liberam!
Equilibrium must be
restored at all costs.
This might be my only chance.
No!
The bond between
celestial wizard and spirit
is out of balance, and only the
Liberam can restore it!
Libra, think!
How can our bond be balanced
if it's completely destroyed?
Arrogant humans...
Even now you
think you have the right
to control our futures.
You won't allow us
even twelve days of freedom.
Some things are worth dying for!
This is precious to us!
You celestial wizards
couldn't possibly understand!
Well I don't understand,
nor do I want to!
There's a difference
between setting yourself free
and throwing your life away!
Freedom shouldn't
come with a death sentence.
That isn't liberation.
It's giving up!
[VIRGO] Enough with
this sentimental blather.
I hate it!
There's no point
explaining to a human.
We don't need your approval!
This is our choice!
[ALL screaming]
You must be terrified by now.
Stop gloating,
ya dumb snake!
Ow! What the heck!
Are you okay?
I ain't gonna feel right
until I get back in the action!
[OPHIUCHUS] What a very
little person you are.
[NATSU] I'll kick your butt
if I can find it!
[groaning in pain]
Natsu, no!
Get out of the way!
But how?!
Perfect timing, man!
How'd you end up
in such a dire situation?
Ate somethin'
that disagreed with me!
[HISUI] Natsu!
Whoa!
Princess, look.
This must be Ophiuchus.
The Snake Charmer spirit.
[HISUI] I didn't think
she'd be so large...
Greetings, Princess.
I'm afraid that you're too late.
Nobody can stop me now.
Omnia... magna...
stella... rex... prae.
Struggle though
you may to tie us down,
we will take what we desire!
That incantation.
She's saying...
"Omnia." Then
"magna stella rex prae."
"All for the sake
of the King of stars."
Well played.
Now tell us what
that really means.
The king that
you're referring to
must be the
Celestial Spirit King.
[HISUI] If all this has
been for the king's sake,
then the spirits haven't
been acting for themselves.
There's something more
at play here.
They're being manipulated.
But what could he
stand to gain from this?
If he's sacrificing his
own subjects then he's lost it.
What is that?
An old book
I borrowed from Yukino.
There's a section
about the Liberam.
If memory serves,
it also mentions a king.
Is the Celestial Spirit
King behind this, or not?
But of course he is.
Ya know, I always wanted
to go toe to toe
with ol' nose hairs.
But I didn't really have a
decent excuse until right now.
[laughing]
How can you defeat my king
when you're about to fall to me?
What's she doin'?
[OPHIUCHUS] I am Ophiuchus,
the Snake Charmer.
Chosen guardian of
the Celestial Spirit King!
I am the thirteenth
spirit of the zodiac.
The deadly shadow of my liege!
Three spirits
still stand strong,
and there is nothing
you can do to stop us!
Aw, man.
She's really lost it.
[LUCY whimpering]
Lucy's in trouble!
Yukino is, too!
Surely there's something
we can do to help.
But they're essentially
trapped in alternate dimensions!
Screw this!
Natsu!
First I'm gonna
thrash this cocky snake
and then I'm gonna
burn the mustache
right off her
dumb king's face!
I warned you
not to interfere.
Now you'll pay the price.
Look out!
What the--
You can leave this to me!
Be careful!
Keep your distance!
This isn't fair!
My frickin' arm
won't do what I tell it to!
Hey Natsu,
I think we need to focus
on the belly
of Ophiuchus's snake!
That glowy spot looks
kinda suspicious, doesn't it?
[NATSU] Yeah.
The rest of the snake's body
is kinda dark and cold,
you know?
So if that spot's warm and
bright, there's a reason why.
Only one way
to find out for sure.
By "only one way,"
I hope you don't mean
"run up and punch it!"
For all we know, that thing
could be chock-full of poison!
This is one of those times
when ya gotta stop thinkin'
and and start swingin'!
I mean just look at that thing.
It's practically beggin' me
to go up there and break it.
[NATSU] Here's my chance!
[screaming]
Looks like you
found a weak spot.
I'll never doubt you again,
I swear.
The light you just targeted...
It must've come from the organ
that was maintaining
the zodiac realms.
Holy...
What did you do?
If you're standing
between me and true freedom,
that makes you my enemy,
no matter what!
No...
The zodiac realms...
They've been
thrown out of balance,
but how can that be possible?
Whoa!
What the heck is going on?
[HAPPY] This is what happens
when you punch first
and ask questions later.
Now Lucy and Yukino
are stuck in that thing!
--But I thought--
--The zodiac realms
are converging.
[OPHIUCHUS] You insect!
How dare you throw
my creations into chaos!
Don't worry, guys,
I got this!
[yelling]
No way...
Whoa!
Lucy! Yukino!
Ground support is on the way!
A mere human
can wield such power?
Oh, I'm more
than just human!
I'm a dragon slayer, got it?
[yelling]
I'm glad to see you,
but how're you here?
I couldn't tell ya.
However...
Now that we can fight together,
there's a certain spell
that comes to mind.
Right!
[BOTH] Oh stars far and wide
that embody the heavens.
By thy radiance,
reveal thy form to me.
I implore Tetrabiblios,
eternal ruler
of the stars above.
[LUCY, YUKINO]
Now that the aspect is complete,
I ask that you
to lend your power to me.
Let your unrestrained rage flow.
And open the raging,
tumultuous gate!
C'mon, before
they finish casting!
There is great
balance in unified action!
It's time for
some punishment!
You shall not prevail!
With all eighty-eight
heavenly bodies.
Shining!
Uranometria!
Let's finish it.
All right!
Is something on your mind?
Could we be in the wrong?
Saving them against their will?
This is right.
[LUCY] Please, Virgo.
When this is over,
turn back to normal.
I'm doing this for you.
I'm sorry.
You deserve a good, long break.
We need to get out of here!
I agree, but how?
Where can we go?
All I know is
that we gotta move.
We'll have to figure out
the rest as we go!
[screaming]
What the--
It looks like
they made it back!
Are they all right?
They pulled it off.
Steady now!
[WENDY] Lucy, please wake up!
Can you open your eyes for me?
We made it?
You can thank
Natsu for that one!
What did he do?
It was quite impressive.
Natsu used his flames
and fused the
zodiac realms into one!
[HISUI] That gave you and Yukino
the chance to join forces!
So you're feeling better?
You don't seem to be
putting out heat anymore.
Yeah, I'm good.
Must've blasted the last of that
darkness magic out of my body.
And hopefully
you've learned to watch
what you eat!
[NATSU] I dunno.
Kinda worked out
for us this time.
Hey snake girl!
Looks like you're
the last spirit standing!
Your assistance
has been invaluable.
I thank you.
[NATSU] Say what?
[OPHIUCHUS]
Shutting all those gates myself
would have been
quite the challenge.
Thank goodness I had you.
[HISUI] Huh?
You've returned all
twelve zodiac members
to the Celestial
Spirit King's grasp!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Are you saying that
the Celestial Spirit King
planned for the
zodiac to be defeated?
He's the one
that stands to gain.
But the plan itself was mine.
The most difficult part
was finding a way
to keep the zodiac spirits
from leaving
the celestial plane.
So I fabricated
a ritual, Liberam,
knowing they
would try to perform it,
but that you would stop them
by sealing their gates.
So the spirits never really
even had a chance at freedom,
and the whole reason
that they were fighting
was just one big lie?
They were tricked into
the whole thing, as were we!
[OPHIUCHUS] The Celestial
Globe serves as a conduit.
It channels power
from the constellations
of the zodiac to my king.
The ritual we set out
to perform's sole purpose
is to grant him
the zodiac's strength.
It's called the "Liberam Verus".
Is there any mention
of it in that book?
There is.
But it'll probably take me more
than a minute to translate it.
Just do it as
quickly as you can.
We need to know
all of the details.
Okay, I'll do my best!
[OPHIUCHUS]
The problem with Liberam Verus
is that it can only sacrifice
spirits in the celestial plane.
Sacrifice? But why?
[OPHIUCHUS]
Becoming an Eclipse spirit
did endow the
Celestial Spirit king,
who was already the
strongest being in his world,
with power greater
than he had ever known.
But it also gave
him an appetite to match.
Fearful of his mighty hunger,
the zodiac spirits attempted
to flee the celestial world.
They strove to be free of him.
But their celestial bodies
pulled them back to the stars.
To resist was to suffer,
and to give in was to die.
The setup was perfect.
With the false hope
of the Liberam,
I set them and you to work
at granting my king
the power he craves.
The Celestial Spirit King
was that affected?
So what I'm
getting out of this
is he's turned
into a mean old lunatic
who nobody
wants to hang out with
'cause he's got
no control of himself!
We thought we were
fighting to protect the spirits,
but we ended up putting them
right into harm's way.
To think we've
been banishing them
to the very place that they were
so desperately
struggling to escape.
A world ruled by
a power-crazed monster.
How awful.
I can't believe this crap!
That isn't the
worst of it, either.
If this demented Celestial
Spirit King goes unchecked...
If his rampage
can't be stopped...
Then the celestial spirit world
will collapse in on itself.
Ya mean the whole damn place?
[OPHIUCHUS] Indeed.
Princess Hisui's prediction
may well come to pass.
[HAPPY] If the
celestial spirit world goes,
then you'll disappear
right along with it, lady!
If it's what my liege
should happen to desire,
then I shall cease
to exist with pleasure!
All is at the will
of his majesty:
The Celestial Spirit King!
[laughing maniacally]
You're willing to die
just to give him more power?
That's friggin' crazy!
[growling noise]
Didja hear that growling?
It sounded
like a wild animal!
[laughing]
Time to move!
Yeah!
[OPHIUCHUS laughing]
Enough of your noise!
You and your king
seem pretty desperate
to get yourselves hurt.
Ya don't need to destroy
a whole world for that.
I got your pain right here!
[HAPPY] Natsu! The Liberam
still hasn't stopped!
[NATSU] Huh...
We'll have to fall back
on our usual strategy.
[HAPPY]
Worked pretty well last time!
[NATSU] And the time before!
In fact, there's nothin' better
when ya don't know
what you're up against!
[HAPPY] Hey! It looks like
Erza and the others
have the same idea!
[NATSU] 'Course they do!
They helped us master it!
[HAPPY]
Heck yeah, they did!
After all, it's Fairy Tail's
most famous tactic!
[NATSU] "Demolish everything!"
[HAPPY, NATSU] Next time:
When the Stars Fall!
[NATSU] All right then, Happy!
When life gives you lemons,
blow 'em up!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!