[NARRATOR] Irene Belserion
stands alongside August
as one of the Alvarez
Empire's mightiest.
It has also been revealed she
is Erza's biological mother.
In her earlier life, she was
known as "Queen of the Dragons,"
as well as creator and first
user of Dragon Slayer magic.
However, the power she unlocked
with this new technique
caused her to transform
into a dragon.
[NARRATOR] Tortured and
desperate to free herself
from this new, monstrous body,
she attempted to enchant
her consciousness
into her unborn child,
with the hopes of gaining
a new chance at life.
Her plan ended in failure,
and the child was left behind.
And after being granted a
human appearance by Zeref,
she now works to
realize his ambition.
The estranged
mother and daughter
now face each other
on the battlefield.
Will Erza's hearfelt
determination be enough
to overcome Irene's
immense magic power?
[ERZA] You may technically
be my mother,
but Fairy Tail is my family.
Anyone who stands between me
and my home will pay the price.
It's interesting.
I thought sharing
your birth story
would spark the smallest
bit of love for you.
Perhaps reawaken my
dormant maternal instinct.
But it didn't work.
All I feel for you is
hostility and disgust.
[ERZA yells]
I became a queen because of
my unparalleled magic power.
You still believe
you can defeat me?
My family gives me power.
You threw that away!
[gasps]
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
Crimson-Black... Twin Blades!
You actually broke my skin.
How dare you.
I'm sorry for what you
went through in your past.
But still, you turned your
back on your only child.
I can't forgive that!
[IRENE] Listen up,
little Dragon Slayer.
Do you remember the "Dragon
Seed" I mentioned earlier?
The thing that took over my body
and made me into a monster?
You have one. It's growing
inside you as we speak.
Yes. I know that.
And I also know that my mother
stopped it from
growing years ago.
So you can't use it to scare me.
She what?
We won't turn into dragons.
We're not like you.
I suppose neither will Natsu.
[LUCY]
Come on! Wake up, please!
[HAPPY]
Just open your eyes!
Natsu. We need you!
[LUCY]
I'm really scared.
Don't you dare give up!
You need to keep calling
to him. Tell him you care.
Otherwise, his life may
slip away forever.
Natsu. Stay strong.
[HAPPY]
Natsu! Come back! Natsu!
[NATSU]
Wait.
Wendy? Gajeel?
Where'd you guys run off to?
[IGNEEL]
I have your answer.
A Dragon Seed.
That is what has been growing
inside of you, Natsu.
It is the curse all Dragon
Slayers are destined to bear.
The seed grows over time.
Eventually, it transforms
its carrier into a dragon.
However, years ago, I halted
the growth of your seed.
It's really you.
[IGNEEL] The seed in
you should remain incapable
of growing any further.
[NATSU]
But did it only work
while your Dragon soul
was in me, too?
[IGNEEL] No. That's not
what's affecting you now.
You should know there is
another seed inside you.
You could call it
a "Demon Seed."
It makes you who you
truly are: E.N.D.
Those two seeds are getting
close to merging--becoming one.
That is the change
you've been feeling,
what's creating such
turmoil in you.
[NATSU]
And that's what's gonna kill me?
When they merge?
[IGNEEL]
Yes. You're going to die.
[IRENE]
I see.
The dragon that cared for
you entered your body
and halted the Dragon
Seed's growth.
The dragon who granted
me my magic, Belserion,
died right before my eyes.
So I took his name,
and swore on my own life
that I would avenge him.
All those centuries of pain,
and now... now I learn it
could've been prevented?
[growling]
It was all for nothing!
I will have my life
restored to me!
I'll leave this body,
and at last be free!
I can put you out
of your misery!
Wendy!
Ready!
All physical abilities up!
Deus Eques!
Very clever.
Separation Enchant Deus Zero!
I'll cancel your Deus Zero
with my own Deus Zero!
Really? This girl casts
high-level enchantments?
[yelling]
[chuckles]
It's over! This is the end!
[ERZA yells]
Now I understand.
At last... I know why the
enchantment on you failed.
[IRENE] I'd thought it was
because you were an infant,
or that our biological
connection got in the way.
Or perhaps the whole
concept was flawed,
and enchanting a
person's identity
onto another was
never truly possible.
The key is compatibility.
I've just realized
that's the only factor
that makes a difference.
[gasps]
[IRENE] And now I've found
someone who's compatible.
A Dragon Slayer
and an enchanter.
One with a youthful body
that will never succumb
to the dragonification.
[gasps]
Wendy!
Ahh. I've waited so
long for this day.
Her magic is a bit weaker,
but I suppose that's fine.
What did you say?
[WENDY] I will have a whole new
life thanks to this body.
Irene Belserion has been reborn.
I'll get used to this.
It shouldn't take much time.
No way!
[WENDY] My left thigh
is slightly injured,
and I seem to be covered
in scratches and bruises.
But I really can't
complain. It works.
What a petite little
thing. So cute!
[ERZA]
What happened to Wendy?
Pay her no mind. She's nothing
but a pile of flesh now.
What have you done with Wendy?
Oh, she's gone.
Or, rather, I suppose
you could say...
...she's here.
Stop this nonsense.
Get out of her
right this instant!
Are you really that
slow-witted, Erza?
This isn't a form of possession!
I have become this
Dragon Slayer.
Your dear mommy has
no use for you anymore.
Despicable!
[gasps]
[WENDY]
Hmm.
My magic power hasn't gone
down as much as I thought.
It seems this little girl is
a wellspring of potential.
I may be a child now,
but playtime is over.
And as you can plainly see,
I'm far too young to
be a mother to you.
I can't truly focus on
the new life ahead of me
until I've completely
erased your existence!
Sky Dragon Slayer magic,
huh? Let me try this out.
[laughing]
I think I like it!
[ERZA screams]
Please, Wendy! You have
to push her out!
[WENDY]
It's no use, Erza.
The girl you knew is dead.
Because as of today, I'm Wendy.
I am Wendy Belserion!
[ERZA]
You're just a parasite.
Hear me? You can't have her!
[ERZA yelling]
Are you sure, Erza?
Can you hurt your friend?
I know all too well the pain
of losing a loved one.
But with our help, you can heal.
Come with us.
Be part of Fairy Tail.
Thanks, Erza!
This time, I'll protect you
for all you've done for me.
You fool!
You're too soft to
survive this war.
[laughs] I've enchanted
your armor.
Explode!
[ERZA screams]
That barely even hurt me.
[gasps]
[IRENE] All attributes...
and resistances up.
Deus Corona.
[IRENE] Since we can both
perform enchantments,
I thought I'd try out your
body-switching trick, too.
Guess it worked.
It took a little while...
but here I am.
Erza, it's me. It's Wendy.
Wendy!
Impossible.
This is different. Heavy.
There's no way!
That little girl was
somehow able to pull off
a full personality enchantment?
I feel so strong. It's great.
I think I'm gonna use
this new power on you.
Teach you a lesson.
Now!
Erza! You should duck!
How?
My old body... used against me?
Separation Enchant.
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH] You can try, but you
won't pull me out of here!
You're wrong.
You said yourself your
new body is weaker.
This girl. Who is she?
Now give it back.
Give back the old me.
This body does have
its advantages.
But I've lived my whole
life being small.
I want my old self back!
Damn you!
What is she--?
Do you still want to have
it back that badly, huh?
It took so long to
be human again!
You hear me? I won't
let you take it!
I'm proud of all my scars.
They're proof I've
fought for what I love.
And they remind me that
even though I suffered,
I still healed.
So go ahead and give me more,
they only make me stronger!
And that body...
remembers the warmth
of every friend
who's comforted me,
held me in their arms.
Wendy!
[growls] Damn you!
Erza?
Wendy! It's really you?
[WENDY]
Yeah. Hey.
If you don't mind,
can you handle the rest?
Sure.
I'll be happy to put
an end to all this.
You're just wretched
little girls.
[ERZA] Trust me, Wendy.
This will be over very soon.
You believe that?
You're in way over
your head, Erza.
I've been building up
my power for centuries!
All that time I protected you.
I held you inside my womb.
And from the moment
you were born,
you've been nothing but a
complete disappointment.
Why must you stand in
the way of my happiness?
I know you've
endured much misery!
But still! I won't
take pity on you!
What the hell do you
know about suffering?
About true misery?
After you abandoned me
in Rosemary village,
I was taken by a cult.
For years I was a slave.
They tried to take my humanity.
I realize it's not
400 years of pain,
but it affected me profoundly.
Changed me.
It's why I'm the
woman I am today!
Why I keep my heart open!
Why I was able to
find my true family.
With their love and care,
I could overcome my pain,
and begin to heal!
Enough of this nonsense.
Your whole existence is
nothing more than a mistake.
I never should've had you!
So now I'll have to kill you!
It's the only way!
[yelling]
No.
[cries]
A-A dragon?
[ERZA gasps]
[screams]
[ERZA]
That was just one hit.
I feel like my bones
are shattered.
[gasps]
[screaming]
Let's see you move now.
[IRENE] As a Sage Dragon,
my power has been amplified
well beyond your imagination.
I possess the supreme form
of enchantment magic:
Master Enchant.
[IRENE] This power
transcends the terrestrial.
The land, the sky, the sea,
everything of this world.
It affects the heavenly bodies.
[ERZA]
No... I can't move.
[IRENE] Now, Erza, prepare
to be obliterated.
I'll turn you into dust!
Deus Sema!
No. Is she truly that powerful?
[ERZA] Jellal uses a
version of this spell.
But this is
exponentially stronger.
There's no way I'll survive it.
What's worse,
it won't only kill me.
Thousands of people
could be wiped out.
Do you see that?
A shooting star?
It's comin' right at us!
[ERZA]
Damn it! I can't just lie here.
I have to move. Come on!
[IRENE] It's over, Erza!
This is how you die!
[laughs]
[ERZA]
I can still move my right arm.
It's all or nothing!
[gasps]
[yelling]
[IRENE] Are you flying
straight into the meteor?
You're speeding up
the inevitable!
[ERZA yelling]
[IRENE] It's pointless!
You can't stop it!
You're just a human!
At some point in time, people
started calling me Titania,
the named shared by a
legendary Fairy Queen.
Honestly, I've never
given that much thought
to what people chose to call me.
But if you're the Queen
of the Dragons...
...then I'll take the name
Titania with pride.
A queen who cherishes her
people and protects them.
I'll do all I can to
help those in need,
even if it ends up
destroying me!
Lend me your strength,
Master! Please!
My daughter...
is she even human?
[LUCY]
Irene unleashes Deus Sema,
a powerful spell that
can control objects
that are not of this world.
With only one arm,
Erza attacks the meteor
hurtling towards the ground,
risking her life to
save countless others.
While the Queen of the Dragons
brings about violence
and hatred,
Titania shares her
love with everyone.
The end of this intense
battle between mother
and the daughter she left
behind is drawing near.
Next Time: "Dragon or Demon."
A warm smile will bring new
life to a dying memory.