[CANCER] Shake me down,
I want to prance!
I've got to move.
It's time to dance!
Oh yeah!
The heck have I done?
Anything but this
I could've dealt with.
[CANCER]
Don't just stand there.
Show me your moves, man!
Eh? What do you mean?
[CANCER]
You know what I mean.
Your hot boogie moves!
You've got them inside!
So let them come play!
[GRAY]
That isn't helpful!
[CROWD cheers]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Now, onto Fairy Tail Cult Quiz,
Question number 5!
This man's name is...
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Nab!
Great. This is going
to be a trick question.
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] But can
anyone tell me his last name?
[LEVY gasps]
[CAPRICORN] Oh dear.
Seems like a very
easy one to me.
They might as well just
give the points away.
Yeah, totally.
She's throwing me
a real softball here!
[LEVY] Oh, dang.
What the heck is his last name?
Nab, uh...
Nab, uh, something.
Come on, brain!
Don't fail me now!
Jonah? No, that's Reedus.
Alors? Is Max's.
Rocko?
Nope, Warren Rocko!
[CAPRICORN] If you'd
like to pass, I'll answer it.
No way I'm going
to pass on this one!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Miss Levy buzzes in!
It's Nab Celery!
[buzzer sounds]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Sorry, but celery is
his least favorite food.
[LEVY gasps]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Yes, Mr. Capricorn!
Nab Lasaro!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Right you are!
[CROWD cheers]
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
Another wrong answer.
You know what that means!
[LEVY whimpers]
Oh, Nab! I'm sorry!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A]
And with that mistake,
the penalty increases!
Holy--!
[HEAVEN VOICE 208A] Let's
keep the game moving folks!
It's on to question number six!
[HAPPY] Gray vs. Cancer!
Dance Battle!
So we're here.
And Loke's nowhere to be found.
M.I.A.
Do you think that he's
hiding somewhere nearby?
[CARLA] There's no shortage
of things to hide behind
in this place.
[NATSU gasps]
[NATSU sniffs[
Is it food?
No food.
But I sure do smell him!
Now, all I've got to do
is follow the scent!
[NATSU sniffs]
[WENDY]
Good idea.
Maybe I can help you with that!
Yeah, me too!
What utter nonsense!
[NATSU sniffs]
[NATSU]
This smells important!
That looks like
the kind of place
we should probably stay out of.
Does it smell like Loke?
[NATSU sniffs]
He definitely went
through this door.
I have a strong feeling
that we're going to
seriously regret going inside.
Well, we got no other choice!
[GILDARTS]
Let's get this started!
I activate the extra
S-Class Wizard bonus!
All wizards will get
a one million increase
in their offensive strength
for the next three turns!
And for a little
something more,
Gildarts gains the power
of invincibility!
Woo!
I'm fired up now!
Well, heck.
I'll take that!
Unacceptable!
No way!
[CANA]
"I'm the rules!", kid!
[SCORPIO scoffs]
[CANA] Gildarts!
Block Aries!
It'll be my pleasure!
[ARIES] This is like,
uber unfair!
Booyah!
There goes your
only spirit in play.
So what're you going to do
about that, you little turd?
[SCORPIO growls]
I suppose it's your turn.
I'm liking this game!
But I just need one more card!
And I'd also like to skip
all that standby crap.
I'll just end
everything on this turn!
I knew there was no
way that you'd lose.
Yep. That's my girl!
Zip it, you!
'Kay...
Battle Sequence time!
Now I'll use the
invincible Gildarts
to clear the whole damn board!
[GILDARTS yells]
No fair!
[SCORPIO grunts]
Way to go, Cana!
That was sweet!
Nicely done!
Thanks for the help!
Well, I am your daddy.
Right, darling?
[CANA chuckles]
[GILDARTS chuckles]
[LUCY grunts]
It's squishing me!
Punishment time!
[VIRGO]
Coochy-coochy-coochy-coo!
--[LUCY gasps]
--Coochy-coochy-coochy...
--[LUCY laughs]
--[LUCY grunts]
--[rumbling]
[LUCY gasps]
Owie!
[VIRGO laughs]
How long until it
crushes your bones?
[LUCY grunts]
[VIRGO]
Coochy-coochy-coochy-coo...
Stop!
[LUCY laughs]
[LUCY] I can't take it!
Are you ticklish here? Or here?
This'll drive you crazy!
[VIRGO]
Coochy-coochy-coochy-coochy...
[LUCY laughs]
[laughing continues]
Wait! Hold on.
Are you stopping?
No. But this isn't
a real punishment.
Huh?
You're enjoying
it more than me!
Are you freaking kidding me?
This is torture!
Let's change.
Hey! Uh, what
do you mean?
I'm in my bikini?!
[VIRGO]
Now, look up here!
[LUCY] Uh! A watermelon?
You're absolutely going to
hate what happens to you next!
Come on, Virgo, can't we just
make up and be friends again?
You are enjoying
this, aren't you?
No way, this is horrible!
[CANCER] Hey, hey,
hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Lemme show you what
I'm working with, man!
[CANCER] This ain't the
time to be standing around.
We've got to get this
boogie battle bumping!
[GRAY]
We've got to do what?!
We're getting down!
You and me are going to
shake it to the rhythm
and step to the beats.
Because it's all about
staying alive tonight!
[GRAY growls]
You want me to dance with you?
[CANCER] Move your
feet to the disco beat!
I've got a feeling this
is going to be sweet!
[GRAY growls]
[GRAY grunts]
I'm screwed!
I've got such
painfully bad rhythm.
I couldn't win a dance
contest to save my life!
[CANCER] Ooh!
He's on his knees, begging
please, but he still looks cool!
So let's get it heated up!
Let's make this place
a disco inferno!
Time put on your
dancing shoes!
[GRAY gasps]
[CANCER] Oh yeah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Here you go, man!
Did you just give
me some shoes?
They're badass
boogie boots!
Once you got on those
hot crimson kicks,
you're going to keep dancin'
until your heart stops
pumping out the beat!
Of course, I gave them just
a little more style for you!
[GRAY]
What the?!
My feet are moving
all by themselves!
[GRAY whimpers]
[GRAY yells]
That's too funky!
[GRAY] Stop now!
I think I'd probably rather die
if it means I can
keep my dignity!
Oh yeah!
That is such a far out
thing for you to say, man!
No. I can't.
I refuse to make
a fool out of myself!
It's a nightmare.
I've got to wake up, right?
It's real.
And it's getting realer!
Cause you got the feeling
deep inside you,
burning a hole in your soul,
it's going to make you twist,
it's going to make you shout,
it's going to make
you lose control!
Free your mind, and
your rump will follow!
Say what?
I'll make you shake
you moneymaker!
[GRAY screams]
Tell me.
What did you do to me?
I just set your spirit
free, brother man.
I cut your heart wide open
so you can get rid
of all that shame!
You cut open my heart?
[GRAYS chatter indistinctly]
I'm feeling so funky.
It's like all these
weird versions of me
are trying to bust out!
No! Stop it!
It's not me!
Oh, I've got
the dopest moves.
Can you dig it?!
Hey, DJ!
Pump up the jams!
[music plays]
[GRAY]
Am I really doing this?
I can't believe it!
[music continues]
Super fly!
[JUVIA gasps]
How strange...
I feel like I'm missing
something amazing right now!
I dance like I fight!
That means I don't fool around.
If you're looking for a
dance battle, you got it!
And you ain't seen
nothing yet, buddy.
Get down, man!
Oh! Those moves are
bringing tears to my eyes!
Ah! Now I've got to
get ready to do my thing.
Got to pick it up
and lay it down!
I like to call this one
the crustacean hustle.
You feel me?
[GRAY]
Not really.
You're barely even moving
your feet over there.
That's pretty slick.
But I'm about to
bring it back retro
with some old school
go-go style.
Please. You're never
going to move forward
if you keep holding
on to the past.
My style is
revolutionary!
I call it...
...the icy slide!
This cat turned my dance floor
into an ice skating rink!
Whoa!
This ain't the way you
do a dance battle, man!
I told you I've got a
revolutionary style, didn't I?
Watch.
See if you can hang
with my cool triple-axel!
[CANCER squeals]
[CROWD cheers]
[GRAY] Gray Bauer!
He's burning up the ice!
[GRAY] Check it!
Gray Spin!
He's got the freshest moves
I've ever seen in my life!
[GRAY] Gray Backspin!
I'm getting
hypnotized!
[GRAY] Graymann Spin!
Those sexy moves!
And now...
Step sequence!
So cool, I'm freezing!
[GRAY] For the finale...
...One hundred gray spin!
[CROWD cheers]
[CANCER]
Oh Yeah!
He's the funkiest thing on ice!
Whoa. That's insane.
I've got to step up my game
if I want to top that!
Let's really get this
party started, man!
Take it up to level two!
So what's different
about this one?
We're firing up a real
dance battle, man!
Huh?
That's what we've been
doing this whole time.
You don't get it.
This dance battle is
about to get real on you!
[CANCER yells]
[GRAY grunts]
[GRAY] Oh, now I see.
You want me to bust some moves
while I bust your head. Hmph
[LIBRA yells]
Please don't do this, Libra!
The last thing I want
to do is fight you!
[LIBRA grunts]
[YUKINO gasps]
[YUKINO sighs]
[LIBRA] Everything's
in equilibrium.
[YUKINO] What's going on?
Where are we?
A place where you
remain in balance, or die.
Die?
[YUKINO]
But I don't understand.
Are you talking about
some kind of balance
between the human world
and the spirit world?
It doesn't make sense to me.
[LIBRA] It will all
become clear in time.
[YUKINO] What?
First, worry about
your own balance!
If you want to keep living!
[LIBRA yells]
[YUKINO growls]
[CANCER]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
[GRAY grunts]
I got styles for miles
and miles, pal.
[GRAY] Ice Cannon!
[CANCER] Heh!
[CANCER] Fresh!
Oh crap!
Come on and play that
funky music, ice boy!
[GRAY]
Ice Make: Lance!
[CANCER]
Oh yeah!
You ain't got nothing
on my crab spin!
Can you dig it?
These pincers of mine
can cut more than rugs, man!
Oh, you want some
more of that, huh?
Ice Impact!
Double Pincers!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
[GRAY GROWLS]
[CANCER]
You're real cool, man.
But there's no way I'm going
to lose to you in my house!
Been waiting' for this one!
[GRAY grunts]
[CANCER gasps]
Hey, this kind of
dancing ain't my style!
You taught me to open up my
heart to new things, remember?
Now it's my turn to
teach you something.
[CANCER]
He's amazing!
First off, I'll show you
the Gray Death Spiral!
[CANCER]
My heart is open.
[GRAY] And now...
The Gray Rolling Jump!
[CANCER]
And he's coming inside!
[GRAY] Gotcha!
Gray Twist Lift, go!
I'm so dizzy I can
barely see straight!
[GRAY] We're making
a great team so far!
[CANCER] This is
like a dream come true!
I'm so happy
I could just die!
Oh yeah?
[CANCER] Huh?
[GRAY] This is going
to be my last routine!
[CANCER]
You're really done?
[CANCER gasps]
[GRAY] Ice Blade.
Seven-Strike Dance!
[CANCER screams]
[CANCER] That's not
a dance, it's a tragedy!
[CANCER groans]
[GRAY] Huh?
[GRAYS chatter indistinctly]
What in the hell
just happened?
Wait.
It's kind of starting
to come back to me now.
Oh man.
Please no.
[CANCER groans]
[CANCER] Come on, man.
Don't tell me your heart
is closed back up again.
Hey.
[CANCER] Yeah?
You tell anyone
about what went down
and I will put you
in a pot and boil you.
You understand me, man?
I know you hate me.
But I still think you're
the coolest dude ever.
Ah, geez.
[CANCER] Good night.
My sweet prince.
[GRAY] I'm just glad
no one had to see that.
[JUVIA]
There's that feeling again.
Like I missed
something incredible.
Okay, so now we're
in a creepy old room.
That looks like
some kind of altar.
Can you still smell Loke?
[NATSU sniffs]
It's like his scent goes this
far and then evaporates.
But the way we came
was the only passageway.
This room seems like
a total dead end to me.
[WENDY] Whoa!
I can definitely feel
a draft coming in
through this crack in the wall!
Maybe it's a secret
door or something!
I'll bet you Loke
crossed through it
because he knew
I was coming after him.
I wonder if we could
get it to open somehow.
Perhaps with a magic word?
[HAPPY] I command you door,
Open sesame, please.
I can get it open.
Stand back everyone.
What?
Seriously?
Fire Dragon.
Iron Fist!
I don't think that
it worked, Natsu!
[HAPPY] Thanks for getting
us killed in here, pal!
Hey, it's not my fault!
[HISUI gasps
Princess!
Guess it did work.
Now let's go get Loke!
That jerk can run.
But he can't hide! Heh, heh.
Do you know what could've caused
that big tremor just now?
I'm not sure.
But it does seem like something
has changed in this room.
Look over there.
A door.
But to where?
Well, I'm not entirely certain,
but I'd be willing to bet
it's somewhere dangerous.
Perhaps a world completely
separate from our own.
What do you think?
We should go.
We still don't know what's
happened in the celestial world.
Our answer might very well
lie behind that door.
Yes.
No matter what perils we may
face on the other side.
I swear on my honor
to be your protector
whatever the cost
may be, princess.
I know you will.
[NATSU] This sucks.
This desert world
is so freaking hot!
[HAPPY] I feel like my fur
is going to melt off.
Hey, I have an idea,
maybe we can get cooler
with some good old
bone-chilling, scary stuff!
[NATSU] Well, it's worth
a shot at least! Boo!
[HAPPY]
Are you kidding me?
[NATSU] No, I'm
trying to scare you!
[HAPPY] Come on, I've fought
monsters and stuff.
It's going to take more
than that to get to me.
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next Time: Juvia vs. Aries!
Desert Death Match!
[NATSU] Maybe we can find Lucy
and she can do one of her skits.
[HAPPY] Geez, I said scare me,
not bore me to death!