[NATSU screams]
[DAN] I can't believe
you fell for that!
[rumbling]
[crash]
Is that all you got?!
Excellent! Now this
is the kinda fight
I've been missin!
♪
[HAPPY] Is this
really the place?
[LUCY] Yeah, I think so.
[LUCY] There's a line in the
"Key of the Starry Heavens"...
"Long and silent
had the key rested,
embraced by the sound
of reverent prayer."
[MICHELLE] By prayer...?
That does suggest
a church of some kind.
Yeah...
But there aren't a lot of
places to hide stuff here.
I'll get an Exceed's
eye view and
see if I can
spot anything.
[NARRATOR] While Natsu's battle
with Dan heats up inside
the tomb, Erza encounters
something truly grotesque
pressed between the shelves
of the Library of Sorcery.
What... is that?
Not... sure.
[BUTT BOSS] YEOW!
Run now!
[WENDY] Whoa...
[CARLA] Who's going
to clean this up?
[jiggling]
[shocked yells]
[HAPPY] True Scoundrels,
Once Again!
No, it's the
Butt Jiggle Gang!
Our Goddess
returned!
I'm so happy!
We missed
you, Wendy!
[ERZA] Don't move!
I take it you're the ones
who did such despicable and
horrific things to Wendy?
Horrific? Us?
Do you deny it?
I'm told you forced her to
dress in a dreadful manner!
[BUTT BOSS] Are you
referring... To her unitard?!
[fart]
What...?! You kept it?!
It was such a
gas seeing her
fill this baby out.
What a rumpin'
good time!
[steel rings]
[BOTH]
She shredded it!
Only monsters
would make a young lady
dress in that fashion! You're
lucky I didn't shred you!
Do you have any idea
what you've done?
Ever since your
last meeting...
Carla's been plagued with
horrible night terrors
that drive her crazy!
[CARLA] It's true... Every night
since then, I've been chased
by a horde of bubble-butted
Wendys in black unitards!
[CARLA] And now that
nightmare... has come to life!
Stay strong, Carla!
[evil chuckle]
[BUTT BOSS] You've
had nightmares, huh?
Lackeys! Huddle up!
[BOTH] Yes, sir!
[BUTT BOSS] Did you
hear that, boys?!
They said we're horrifying!
[BUTT LACKEY A] Yeah and
we scarred their house cat
for life! That practically
makes us living legends!
[BUTT LACKEY B] I've got a
rumblin' deep down that needs
to be shared! I say it's about
time we go loud and proud, boss!
[BUTT BOSS] We can't
crack the seal yet...
Just play it cool for now.
Your fear is only
natural, kitty cat...
For you are in the
presence of true scoundrels!
[ALL THREE] The
Butt Jiggle Gang!
[CANA] Yeah, the name's not as
terrifying as you think it is.
[CARLA] If you're done
waving your rears at us,
you can start cleaning up
the colossal mess you made!
[ALL THREE] Hmm?
[BUTT BOSS] Well,
you heard the lady...!
Get to cleanin', lackeys!
[BUTT LACKEY B] But you're the
one who knocked 'em over, boss!
Back talkin' me?!
Just for that, you get
thirty-six push-ups!
But, Boss!
Shouldn't it
be forty sir?
I'm wai-ting!
[BOTH] One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine! Ten! Eleven!...
They're so... dumb.
Is this a comedy act?
[BUTT BOSS] I think they're
trying to insult us!
Just for that, we're gonna
take their treasure by force!
Now that's how a true
scoundrel would do things!
[BUTT LACKEY B] You're
so inspiring, Boss!
Is there a reason you
stopped doing push-ups?
[BOTH]
We just finished!
What exactly are
you doing here?
Well...
you can't stop us, so I
might as well tell you.
We know all about Fairy Tail's
hunt for a super treasure
that'll turn the
world on its head.
Every scoundrel's
out lookin' for it!
We're gonna snatch it
and rule the world!
Then no one's
gonna look down
their noses at us again.
[WENDY] Stop it!
Carla!
Why are you
wearing that?
[WENDY] I knew I might run
into them again someday,
so I prepared accordingly.
At last! Our goddess
has returned to us!
It's like a ray
of sunshine.
She was the wind
beneath our wings.
[WENDY] Did you already
forget everything I told you
the last time we met?
You should stop your pursuit
of being true scoundrels
and invest in your future!
I know that, deep down,
there are good men inside you...
and they're just waiting for the
chance to break out and be free!
Don't deny your true
selves a chance
to breathe fresh air!
Don't deny our...
true selves?
Think back
for a moment...
Remember when
you were children?
Those were
simpler times.
You could run and play with
your friends until sundown.
You could share your
laughter and dreams
and not worry
about tomorrow.
Embrace your true selves,
and you can enjoy
that happiness again!
[CARLA] Please tell me she's
not being serious about this.
[CANA] I dunno, she looks
pretty freakin' serious to me.
God-ess!
Whadda we do now?
Have we been living
a lie all of this time?
Are we really just farts in
the mighty wind of destiny?
[BOTH] No, sir!
We know that deep
down we're true scoundrels
and we embrace it in
all of its gaseous glory!
Before you
start judgin' us,
you should spend a
day... in our unitard!
Show us the Butt Jiggle
Gang's "true self"!
What are you
asking me?
I'm telling you, if
we're supposed to be
playing by your rules,
then the least you could do
is show some respect and
follow one of ours. Fair?
Erza! Don't do it!
Fine.
You're doing
it? Okay...
Where'd the
flower come from?
It's a little souvenir
from our picnic earlier.
And It smells
as nice as it looks.
It does add a ladylike touch
to that plain ol unitard.
Wow! This is
surprisingly comfortable.
We are not
amateurs!
[ERZA] It's obvious you
care about aesthetics...
But I'm curious; does your
pride for these suits
go deeper than just
their appearance?
What's that?
[ERZA] Simple...
If you're truly the
scoundrel you claim to be...
It'll reflect in
the way you think.
Therefore, I will conduct
a test of your scoundrel-dom.
Start by reciting the finer
points of your philosophy.
Uh... Erza...? Do you
really think we can afford
to be wasting that kind
of time with these guys?
No... But these
misguided fools need to be
taught a lesson.
And I intend to make sure
they learn it well,
even if it takes all day.
If that fails, I'll
simply beat it into them.
[WENDY] Now's
our chance.
It might sound crazy
but I think this is all
a part of
Erza's plan.
Why else would she
be egging 'em on?
I get the feeling she's trying
to distract them so we can
go looking for
the clock piece.
Are you sure
about that?
It looks like she's just
really into it to me.
Well either way,
Wendy's got a point...
And we've gotta take advantage
of this opportunity.
[CANA] Here,
keep this with you.
The moment I find the clock
piece, this'll let you know.
[WENDY] Right!
You're staying?!
Well yeah, I am
their goddess!
What...? No... Don't tell
me you like that getup!
We better get goin'.
[CANA] I'm startin' to
think the Legion Platoon
is the source of the leak.
That's what I said.
This is the second
time we've been stopped
by wannabe bandits
on this mission...
Maybe that was
their plan all along.
[CARLA] Perhaps they're
causing the very "chaos"
we've been worried about.
There's no point
fretting about it...
Let's just focus on what
we can do here and now.
"Upon the knowledge of
age-old sorcery time does rest."
Looks like we found the
spot Lucy told us about.
It matches the clue.
And I think this might be
where we should start looking.
Are you sure we'll
find it here?
[CANA] The Library of Sorcery
is the only place you can
find books full of old magic
and techniques like these.
Printing technology
didn't exist when most of them
were transcribed; which
means there are a lot of
hand-written manuscripts.
And all of these books
in this section are about
ancient magic, so it seems
like the best place to start.
[CARLA] So the clock piece has
to be somewhere among them.
[CANA] Talk about a
needle in a haystack...
[collapsing buildings]
[NATSU] Fire Dragon... Roar!
[DAN] Now I can't
believe I fell for that!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon...
Iron Fist!
[DAN laughs]
Is somethin'
funny, tough guy?
[DAN] Yeah, your magic
power... It's so weak.
Huh?!
I've been thinking about it
ever since our last fight...
Seems like your offensive power
is more for show than anything.
Say what?!
Samuel mentioned
something interesting...
Is it true you were
frozen in time on an island
for seven years?
I'd be willing to bet the
farm that's the reason
you'll never be
able to beat me.
You wanna test that?
[DAN] You don't get it do
you? While you were frozen,
I had seven years
to improve my skills!
I'm a completely different
caliber of wizard...
A seven year old fossil
ain't got nothing on me!
Keep talkin' 'cause
it'll make pounding you
even sweeter!
It'd take you seventy
years to match me in power!
If you want proof,
I can give ya a taste!
Fire Dragon... Brilliant Flame!
Nice try!
[grunts and groans]
What the...
[crashes]
[explosion]
[groans]
Natsu?!
[HAPPY]
What happened?
You okay?!
[armored footsteps]
[DAN] So that's where you
were hiding, Looly baby!
[LUCY] Not him again!
[HAPPY] He loves
those silly pet names.
Gimme some sugar!
I've had enough of you!
Butt-out! Gimme
a second, man!
[shocked gasp]
Serves you right for gettin'
in my way, ya pipsqueak!
[NATSU, high-pitched] I'll
pip your squeak, jerk wad!
[DAN] Now then,
where were we?
[LUCY] Stay awaaaay!
You heard the lady!
I guess you're not a quick
learner either, kid. Too bad!
[screams]
Natsu!
[HAPPY] Uh-oh... My bad...
Happy...? Are you
doing that on purpose?
Not you, too,
Michelle!
[sobbing]
[BUTT LACKEY B] I never
knew our uniforms
held such a
deep secret!
Don't you forgetit!
This suit is your life!
[BOTH, sobbing] Yes, Boss!
[WENDY] What should we do
now? His story was so bizarre
I'm not really sure
how to respond to it.
[ERZA] Are you
kidding me?
What a lame story. As a
kid, you spilled something
on your shirt, so you
smeared black ink
all over it to hide the
stains and avoid punishment?
Honestly, I find
it ridiculous.
It's a prime example
of scoundrel-dom!
[ERZA] Nonsense! You are
hardly a scoundrel at all.
[BUTT BOSS] What was that?!
You heard me... A true
scoundrel wouldn't
allow his men to be so
emotionally dependent.
If you insist on calling
yourself their leader...
then you must strive to set
the highest example possible!
Hey, let's not forget
why we came here, okay?
On the ground!
One hundred push-ups!
A hundred?!
Yes, if you're going to
force your men to do them...
then you need to
set an example first!
Or are you a
half-hearted scoundrel?
If you aren't, you'll give
me a full hundred, easy!
This is your chance
to prove me wrong!
You little fart!
Just butt out would ya?
Beat her!
Remember, you're the one
bringing the stench!
So serve her up a
pungent dose of reality!
But a true scoundrel
wouldn't care
about a challenge from-
[BOTH] Please, Boss, you
have to beat her! For us!
[BUTT BOSS] Those
puppy dog expressions!
They're tearing
up my insides!
I can't take it!
All right, men...
I'll do it for you!
Now watch
closely, boys...
I'm only doin'
this one time!
Just look
at him go!
That's our
boss for ya!
'Scuse me... You might
want to pace yourself
a little bit.
[NARRATOR] It seems
the Library of Sorcery
is in a state of confusion.
Meanwhile... Lucy and
her team find themselves
dealing with confusion
of a different sort...
[DAN] Keep shootin' at me...!
All you'll end up doin' is
bringing these ruins down
on top of your thick skulls!
He's got a point,
we can't use magic!
Put it away, Romeo.
Crap!
[DAN] Loopsy!
Looks like we've
got a chapel now...
Let's consummate our marriage
in the presence of God!
[LUCY screams]
I'm outta here!
[DAN] Don't fight it!
[ROMEO] Leave her
alone, ya creep!
[LUCY] Don't just stand there!
We have to do something!
We need to try and get
him out of the building,
if we can.
He doesn't
know the clock piece
might be hidden in here, so we
still have a chance to get it.
But how are we supposed
to pull that off?
I've got an idea!
I think I have
the same idea.
[LUCY] Awesome!
Let's hear it then!
[NATSU] Aw, I want
in on it, too!
[BOTH] You'll
act as the bait!
Bait...? For what?
[HAPPY] We have to get Dan
to lower his guard somehow!
[MICHELLE] And you're
the obvious choice!
[NATSU] Come on! Just do it!
You're suggesting...
what exactly?
Matrimony!
Not happening!
[MICHELLE] But we need
you to turn his feelings
for you against him!
I'll do it.
[LUCY] Dan!
[DAN] Yes... Looeypie?
Please... take me away.
[HAPPY] What's up?
[MICHELLE] I don't think
she was sexy enough.
[HAPPY] Yeah... We might
be askin' too much of her.
[heart throbbing]
[DAN] Oh, yeah! Blast off!
[DAN] Love me!
[giggles] Catch me
if you can, darling!
Oh, you know I
will, butter cup!
And then I'm gonna...
We got him!
Quick, while
he's distracted!
'Kay Natsu!
Now's your chance!
[NATSU] Hurry and get
me above him, Happy!
Aye, Sir!
[LUCY giggles]
When it comes to
strength, you might have
an advantage over me one-on-one.
But when we all work together...
Even the
strongest wizards
can't hold a candle
to us! Romeo!
[ROMEO] Here!
Fire Dragon...
Iron Fist!
Now that's
how it's done!
Aw yeah!
[LUCY] Phew!
I like him much better
when he's passed out.
[LUCY] What the-?!
[MICHELLE] The wall is shining!
[LUCY] Whoa!
[NATSU] That thing's gigantic!
[ROMEO] What is it?
[LUCY] It's the clock piece!
[NATSU] So that's
where it was hiding!
[MICHELLE] Natsu's last
attack must've caused it
to be revealed!
You got two birds
with one stone!
Well yeah, that was
my plan the whole time kid!
Yeah, sure... We
finally found one!
We're still
in the game.
[HAPPY sobs]
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm just so proud cuz
this is the first time
one of Lucy's seduction
plans worked!
[LUCY] It was your plan,
you walking hair ball!
[HAPPY sobs]
At last...
I've found it!
[BUTT BOSS] Thir...
ty... eight...!
[BUTT LACKEY A]
Hang in there, Boss!
[BUTT LACKEY B] You can
do it! Just sixty more!
[BUTT BOSS]
Nope... I'm pooped.
[ERZA] You're nothing
but talk, after all.
[WENDY] Maybe you
should rest a bit.
I ain't outta gas yet!
The Butt Jiggle Gang's true
power lies... In these babies!
Get ready to
drop a load!
[LACKEYS] Right!
[ALL] Gas Butt
Triple... Ecstasy!
[WENDY] Erza! Look out!
[massive fart]
[farts]
[rumbling]
My nose is burning!
[CARLA] I was hoping I'd never
have to smell that again.
[CANA screams]
[CARLA] Cana! Are you okay?
[CARLA] Hey look...!
What's that?!
[CANA] A secret passageway...
[CANA running]
Guess we have that
stench to thank for this!
We'll see... This path
could lead to a trap!
[CANA] I think we
just struck gold.
[CARLA] Well what
do you know...?
I suppose we should be thanking
that horrible smell, after all.
[evil laugh]
Now do you
realize our power?
[ERZA] What a...
crude technique...
[ringing]
Looks like Cana and Carla
found the clock piece!
[BUTT BOSS] The treasure,
huh? In that case...
[BUTT BOSS yells]
[fart]
[BUTT BOSS] Try
Point-blank... Ecstasy!
[massive fart]
[WENDY] Erza, No!
[WENDY sobs]
[CARLA] So... how are we
supposed to carry it?
[CANA] Uh... well... hmm...
Gas 'em!
[farts]
[rumbling]
[explosion]
[laughs]
[BUTT BOSS] Howdya like that?!
Butts talk and
losers walk, ladies!
[yells]
Do you know
what you've done?
You've destroyed one of
my precious memories!
[ERZA cries]
Divine Retribution!
[BUTT BOSS] You haven't
smelled the last of us!
[WENDY] They're gone now.
[CARLA] Hopefully
for good this time.
[CANA] You alright?
You seem out of it.
[ERZA] I'm still reeling
from their attack.
Well, now that
we have this...
How are we supposed
to carry it?
[ERZA] Huh?
Oh, that's easy...
I can pack it along with
the rest of my things.
[LEVY] Why haven't
we found it yet?
Prob'ly 'cause
you're workin' your mouth
instead of your arms!
[JET] He's got some nerve
talkin' to Levy like that!
[DROY] Yeah, but we need him
to find the clock piece.
Is something wrong?
[GAJEEL] I get the
feelin' we're not alone.
Uh-oh...
[DROY] Where are they?
Can you tell?
[SAMUEL] Well... It appears
that I've been spotted.
[LEVY] He's with
the Legion Platoon!
[GAJEEL] Why are you here?!
[SAMUEL] That
should be obvious...
We're after the
same thing, aren't we?
I've come to claim it.
♪
[HAPPY] Alright, it's
time for a Bro Test:
You and I are both hungry,
and there are two fish
in front of us.
What would you do?
[NATSU] I'd eat two fish.
[HAPPY] What if
there were four fish?
[NATSU] Then I'd eat four.
[HAPPY] Whoa! Epic Bro fail!
Are you trying to tell me
you'd let your 'lil
buddy starve to death?!
[NATSU] Whaddya mean?
I'd save some for ya!
[HAPPY] You've heard
of math before, right?
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next Time:
Defying Calculation!
[NATSU] Okay, look, if I eat the
meat and you eat the bones
then both of us get
half of each fish, right?!
[HAPPY] It takes guts
to be that stupid. Bro pass.