[WARREN gasps]
How in the hell were we not able
to see them approaching earlier?
All members, prepare for battle!
They're coming from the sky!
Approximately 50 full-size
aerial cruisers!
[ERZA]
Nakagami...
...Starlight!
Owie!
Sucker punch?
[MAKAROV] We've managed to fend
off the first wave of attacks.
However, the fact remains that
we're facing enemy forces
coming at us from
every direction.
That's true, but now
we have support
from every other guild in Fiore.
No worries with them in
the fight. We got this!
Hold on.
This is a matter for
Fairy Tail to resolve.
I had hoped to keep
our fellow guilds
out of this confrontation.
[LAXUS] That kind of
attitude is only gonna
get us killed, ya know?
Ishgar's getting turned
into a warzone,
so every guild on its
soil has to fight.
And as for me, I'll start
by stompin' the guy
that attacked the
Thunder Legion.
I believe Laxus makes a
valid point, First Master.
We should accept help
from the other guilds
with gratefulness in our hearts,
and devise a new
strategy accordingly.
Warren, give me
a situation report.
[WARREN]
I'm on it, Master!
So, this Magic Sealstone,
it really stops her
from using magic?
Well, she's not causing
any trouble right now.
Seems like it's working
pretty well to me.
[BOTH grunting]
I probably shouldn't
stare at her like that!
Is it a normal thing
for western girls
to wear such skimpy outfits?
She dresses like Bisca.
[gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
I suppose that's not your
typical mom attire, is it?
I think we should
maybe try to make sure
she's in a bit more
"flattering" pose.
Maybe so!
It could be more comfortable,
and she could look
her very best, too!
Stop being gross!
Owie!
Master said that we're to
treat any prisoners we take
with respect, remember?
[CANA] Look away for a second
and this is what happens.
[MACAO, WAKABA]
We're sorry!
[LUCY]
Time for the truth.
I need to know if you have some
kind of connection to my mother.
There has to be a reason
why you called me
"Layla's Daughter"
back at my place.
[BRANDISH]
I'm not telling you anything.
If you're gonna
kill me, kill me.
We don't do that kind
of stuff to our prisoners.
Tell me, how do you know my mom?
Only thing I'll tell you is you
should kill me while you can.
Bringing me into your guild hall
like this was a major mistake.
One you won't live to regret.
You're wasting your
time with her.
[MARIN]
So that's the enemy's base, huh.
Where they're holding
my lady against her will.
Since I can control
the Law of Space,
I'll have no problem
getting inside.
[INVEL]
Your Majesty.
It would appear that both Ajeel
and Brandish have been defeated.
[YAJEEL]
They have?
[chuckles]
That's fine. We have to keep
this fun and competitive.
Right, Mavis?
I'm shaken by this.
My dearest grandson falling
in battle so quickly...
So two of the Twelve
have already been killed.
Most shocking.
I assure you, they're
very much alive.
Which highlights another
of our foe's weaknesses.
[alarm blaring]
[WARREN]
Ah!
There's a dire
situation to the east!
Almost every guild in Bosco
has been decimated!
Oh, no!
How can so many guilds
be taken down by one army?
That's terrifying!
I don't know if their goal
was to take control of Bosco,
but it seems like they've
stopped their advance for now!
There is some good news though!
The enemy army coming
from the north
is about to be met by
Sabertooth and Blue Pegasus!
[WARREN] And although the
invaders from the south
have taken the port of Hargeon,
Mermaid Heel and Lamia Scale are
on their way to drive 'em out!
They've got it covered!
So that just leaves us
to deal with the forces
coming from the east and west!
Well, hopefully that'll
be the case.
But there's no guarantee
they'll be able to stop them.
Hey! Try to have a little
faith in our allies, would ya?
Come on! We gotta go
and help our friends!
He's right.
If they're coming to our aid,
we can't just sit here and let
them do all the fighting for us!
We gotta jump in there and
man the front lines with them!
Of course. We'll
form some squads.
Mirajane, you, Elfman, Lisanna,
Gajeel, Levy, and Lily
will take the north!
Manly squad!
This isn't a favor to
Jenny, but glad to help!
We can handle 'em!
Yeah!
I've wanted to arrest
Sabertooth anyway.
Nope. That's not
gonna happen, Gajeel.
And providing support
to the south
will be Natsu, Gray, Juvia,
Wendy, Carla, and Laxus.
I guess that means
we're gonna be seein'
my old buddy Lyon again.
To be perfectly honest,
I'd rather not.
If I go south, I can crush that
mechanical freak's real body.
It'll be great to be
with Shelia again!
Yes, the Sky Sisters
back in action!
[WENDY]
Mh-hm!
Hang on. Where's Natsu?
I could've sworn
he was here with us.
[WIZARD D] Did he seriously
bail on us to do his own thing
at a time like this?
Natsu!
[WIZARD F]
Natsu! Where are you?
[FAIRY TAIL shouting]
Wherever he is, he's doing
what he needs to do!
Erza!
I volunteer to go
south in his place.
I'd love to see Kagura.
But you're still too injured!
[LUCY]
Hope he's okay.
Lucy and Cana, you'll stay here
to watch over the prisoner.
Oh. Yes, ma'am!
Definitely don't wanna leave her
alone with those old creepers.
[MACAO, WAKABA]
Come on.
Everyone else will
defend the guild hall.
There's still a high probability
of a surprise attack.
Agreed.
But what of the forces coming
in from the east and west?
The western army is moving much
more slowly than the others.
Which means... that's likely
where Zeref is coming from.
We'll have to deal with the
other three groups first.
Once they've been neutralized,
we'll fend him off with
everything we've got left.
[ROMEO]
Yeah.
Okay then. You can send me
to the eastern front!
The eastern army poses the most
imminent threat right now.
Given the situation,
we must counter them
with the strongest
fighters we can find.
[ROMEO]
And who would that be?
I assume that we're
in contact, Warren?
Yes, ma'am! Fiore's mightiest
are ready for action!
The Four Emperors of Ishgar!
That's so cool!
I never saw this coming!
I feel kinda bad for them since
they've all been working so hard
to avoid going to war.
But it seems to me like
there was nothing
they could really do about it.
A pretty awkward
position to be in.
If the enemy is somehow able
to fight their way past them,
there isn't a soul in Fiore that
can hold back the invasion.
[MAVIS]
We're counting on you, Warrod.
[WIZARD M]
Whoa! Look! Do you see that?
[WIZARD H]
It's gotta be Natsu!
It looks like we found him!
[WIZARD I]
Check out how fast he's moving!
Really? Come on.
Stop, you fool!
My lord. There is an object
approaching at high speed.
You ready to finish
this, Zeref? Let's go!
[LISANNA]
Oh, no.
Does Natsu think he can take
on Zeref all by himself?
That's manly, but reckless!
What an idiot.
We should go back
him up. He needs us!
You're right! I'll go, too!
[ERZA]
Hold on!
We're all concerned,
but we must stick to
the First Master's plan.
Leave Zeref in Natsu's hands.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Zeref's power is legendary.
And he's got the Book of E.N.D.
That may be true,
but Natsu told us that he has
the means to defeat him.
Because my right arm...
is a secret weapon, too.
I have no doubt he will.
As usual, you're putting too
much faith in that hot head!
Get real!
You guys?
Oh, Gray.
[ERZA]
That so?
Meaning you don't
have faith in him?
All right! The two of you
need to cool it down!
So then, what do we do?
We'll trust in Natsu.
I realize that it might seem
like a reckless strategy,
but there is some
logic at its core.
At the moment, we're
completely surrounded.
Dispatching their leader
and ending the battle
as early as possible
might prove to be an effective
way out of this situation.
So, Gray. I want you
to believe in him, too.
[GRAY] Ugh. It's not
like I don't, ya know?
I'm worried 'cause I don't
like him goin' alone.
Did you actually admit to
being worried about Natsu?
[CARLA]
He isn't alone.
He's got somebody with him.
Happy.
[HAPPY] All right,
Natsu. There they are.
Yeah.
[HAPPY]
There's so many of 'em!
[NATSU]
Looks like a big black carpet.
And they're tryin' to roll
the thing right into our house.
Hey, that reminds me.
Whatever happened to that
dirty ol' rug we used to have?
What do ya think happened?
You burned it up.
Oh, yeah!
Not a bad idea!
Take us in, Happy!
[HAPPY]
Aye, Sir!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS screaming]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER A]
What the hell?
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER B]
Enemy attack!
[NATSU]
Let's do another one!
[HAPPY] You seriously
wanna fight all of 'em?
Yeah! If that's what it
takes to drag Zeref out!
[yells]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS gasp]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER F]
You're dead!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER G]
I'll kill you myself!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS yelling]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER I]
He knocked it away!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER J] So what?
Fire! Don't let him get closer!
[gasps]
Natsu!
[NATSU]
I'm fine!
I gotta protect all our friends.
So that means I gotta fight!
Fire Dragon King... Roar!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS screaming]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER K]
He just burned away the ground!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER L]
That guy is a monster.
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER K] No one said
anything about fighting someone
with that much power!
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER L gasps]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER K] How many
of ours did he take out?
[ZEREF] Nine hundred
and seventy-three men.
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS gasp]
[ZEREF]
Which leaves 999,027 remaining.
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS chattering]
You got here quickly.
That works for me.
I was quite eager to come
and say hello, Natsu.
You're just in time
to say goodbye, Zeref.
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER N]
Did you hear that?
I think he called
His Majesty "Zeref"?
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER O]
Zeref?
That's His Majesty's
name in Ishgar.
[ALVAREZ SOLDIER O]
General Invel.
[INVEL] They call him
the Black Wizard Zeref.
Perhaps that is his true name.
Sorry, but you'd better
give us some space.
You should get back, Happy.
[HAPPY]
Aye.
[HAPPY] He's planning to
use it right off the bat.
Good luck, Natsu!
In fact, you should all retreat
several kilometers to the west.
Are you going to
engage this fool?
Your power is wasted
on one such as him.
[ZEREF]
I am the only one who can.
Now, men! Retreat to the west!
His Majesty will clear
the path for us!
You're not gonna get Mavis.
[ZEREF] The only reason
we've reached this point
is because you failed
to destroy me.
I can hear you talkin',
but I don't have a clue what
in the hell you're saying.
Not that I care.
[gasps]
[ZEREF] What is this magic
power? This blistering heat?
[chuckles]
Here goes!
[NATSU yells]
My spell vanished.
Like he burned it away!
[groaning]
[yelling]
That's the way! Show 'em
how it's done, Natsu!
[growls]
[ALVAREZ SOLDIERS gasping]
How very surprising!
Seems you've developed
a new skill.
[NATSU]
My father Igneel gave it to me.
[ZEREF]
Hm?
This is the last of his power.
I've been holding it.
I spent ten months in training
just so I could release it now.
The last of his power, you say?
That's right. I have
to make it count.
Because once it's gone,
it'll never come back.
Every last bit of Igneel's
determination in one shot.
[IGNEEL roars]
[ZEREF] This power is
the will of the dying.
Maybe... that's what I needed.
What finally ends the pain... of
one who's cursed to never die.
Mode: Fire Dragon King!
[ZEREF] He's turned the
ground itself to fire!
Incredible!
This is the end, Zeref! Goodbye!
[ZEREF] After what's
felt like an eternity,
my wish shall be granted.
[ZEREF]
Thank you.
Igneel...
Anna...
Layla...
Mavis...
And...
...my dear little brother...
[ZEREF]
Natsu.
[LUCY] The tenacious
flame given to Natsu
by his father, Igneel,
King of the Fire Dragons,
burns the black wizard's body.
Sensing death's arrival,
Zeref begins to reveal the
Dragon Slayer's secret origin,
a tale Natsu has never heard.
This shocking truth sends
Natsu into a frenzy,
fists swinging with
uncontrollable rage.
But is his goal to
protect or destroy?
Next Time: "Across 400 Years."
A demon of the Book of Zeref
returns to his creator at last.