Ha.
I love your eastern
kimono. It's beautiful.
However...
...I'm afraid your blood
is going to stain it.
[KAGURA] No. Where is all this
magic power coming from?
[gasps]
[KAGURA]
Her power is so intense.
The entire battlefield
is frozen in terror.
She has to be a member
of the Spriggan Twelve.
Your bangs kind of
remind me of Randi's.
Now this will be fun.
[KAGURA]
Huh?
I didn't see her.
[BRANDISH groans]
Wait, where am I?
[LUCY]
The infirmary.
Sorry, but Master insisted
that we leave those on you.
Hopefully they should be at
least a bit more comfortable
now that they're not
behind your back, though.
[BRANDISH]
Where's Marin?
You mean, Mister "A-Plus"?
He's locked up.
[CANA]
Right where he belongs.
Freakin' psycho was tryin'
to choke you to death.
You owe your life to
these young ladies.
They saved you for
some reason. So...
Why did you help?
[CANA]
Ugh. Think about it, would ya?
It's because you couldn't
tell us anything
if you'd just croaked
on the floor down there!
[BRANDISH] I still won't
tell you anything.
Well, besides that,
we really don't want anybody
to die on our watch.
Not even our enemies.
[BRANDISH] Great, so
you'll just torture me.
We don't do that stuff either.
I will if you want me to!
Cana!
I mean, we took a bath
together, didn't we?
I dunno. I just don't feel
like you're an evil person.
I'll tell you everything
I know about Layla.
[gasps]
On two conditions:
Lose these and allow me to
talk to Lucy in private.
I think you may be
overplaying your hand here.
No, it's fine. I'll let
her have that, for now.
Very well then. Suppose
we'll leave you be.
I'll remove the chain,
but the Sealstone stays on.
[CANA] If she tries anything,
you just holler. Okay, Lucy?
First off, my full
name is Brandish Mu.
My mom's was Grammie.
She was a servant, and
worked for Layla Heartfilia.
When your mother quit being
a Celestial Spirit wizard,
she entrusted three of her keys
to her most loyal servants.
The key for Capricorn
went to Zordio.
Cancer went to Supetto.
Sweet old Supetto!
[BRANDISH]
And as for my mom,
she was given the key that
unlocks Aquarius' gate.
Mom had a lot of
respect for Layla,
and that key was her most
treasured possession,
without a doubt.
She took great care of it and
even polished it every day.
But still, somehow, it must've
not been good enough,
because your mother
betrayed her.
Huh? How so?
Tell me, exactly where did
you get the Aquarius key?
Well, from Mom.
But she'd given it to
my mother years before.
So how could she have possibly
passed it along to you?
It's easy.
She simply took the key back
after she murdered my mother.
[gasps]
No way. That's crazy.
You're so hopelessly naive.
Reality is not what you
choose to believe in.
[LUCY screams]
You also need to learn to
not blindly trust people.
[LUCY]
Please.
[BRANDISH]
Sorry it has to be this way,
but I can't take revenge
on Layla herself.
Since your mom's dead,
I'll have to get my
vengeance by killing you.
Just give up.
And die.
[LUCY grunting]
[BRANDISH gasps]
Are you telling
stories about my key?
Aquarius, it's you.
Long time no see, Lucy.
I thought you'd
never come back.
It's a miracle!
I missed you so much.
Calm down. I'm not
back for good.
About a year after
my key was broken,
a new one appeared
somewhere in the world.
This will allow a human to
open my gate once again.
Anyway, even though no one
has made a new
contract as of yet,
the Celestial Spirit King
granted me passage
into this world.
However, I can't stay long.
[gasps]
Okay.
At least I get to see your
face again, so I'm happy.
And it's been even longer
for us. Huh, Brandish?
[LUCY]
You know her?
Yeah, of course I do.
Didn't she tell you her mother
had my key for a little while?
The two of us really had
some fun times together
back in the old days, didn't we?
[grumbles]
Listen, you brat!
When someone asks you
a question, answer it!
Yes! Forgive me.
Please, mistress!
[LUCY]
Whoa. What is going on here?
I always knew you'd grow up to
be some kinda twisted chick
and I'll bet that nasty attitude
has kept the boys
away, hasn't it?
[BRANDISH]
Yes, ma'am.
[LUCY]
Uhh...
Been forever since I've
seen a good dog impression.
[BRANDISH barking]
Now there's a good girl.
Thank you, kind
mistress. Woof!
So behave!
Thank you, kind
mistress, I will!
Okay. That's weird.
[AQUARIUS]
In case you've forgotten,
I'm your master,
and Lucy is mine.
You understand what that
means, don't you, Brandish?
[BRANDISH]
I do, but nevertheless,
I can't forgive Layla
for killing my mother.
Someone has to pay for that!
I hope you realize how
stupid that sounds.
Besides, Layla
wasn't responsible
for Grammie's death
in the first place.
[BOTH gasp]
That's why I'm here.
To tell you the truth
about what happened.
Or more accurately,
to show you what happened.
What's going on?
We're mermaids?
[LUCY]
Hey, Aquarius! Care to explain?
We're inside the
Memory of the Stars.
A place where the memories
of the Celestial Spirits
are archived.
This may feel like a dream,
but let me make it
abundantly clear
that everything you see and
hear is exactly as it happened.
Follow me.
[LUCY]
Somebody's down there!
[AQUARIUS]
That's Anna Heartfilia.
She was your ancestor
and also a powerful
Celestial Spirit wizard.
[AQUARIUS]
Four hundred years ago,
an ambitious plan
was put into action
with the Black Wizard,
the dragons,
and the Celestial magic
users working together.
Is that Zeref?
Emperor Spriggan?
The plan was to send warriors
created to defeat
Acnologia into the future.
The time travel
was made possible
by a special kind
of magic: Eclipse.
Originated in the
Celestial world.
Anna opened this
door to the future,
and for generations,
the Heartfilia family waited
until the time came to unseal.
But what were they waiting for?
For the Eclipse to work,
you need to have one
Celestial Spirit wizard
stationed at the entrance
and one at the exit.
This plan needed the
exit set in a future
with enough Ether-nano to fuel
the warriors passing through,
but no one in your family knew
when that time would come,
so they waited.
As it turned out,
the Eclipse was ready
during Layla's generation.
[LUCY]
Mom!
[AQUARIUS]
Opening the gate required
all twelve of the Zodiac keys.
[AQUARIUS] Unfortunately,
Grammie had moved to Alakitasia,
and because of the distance,
Layla couldn't reach her in time
to get back my
key for this task.
So to compensate for the
missing magic power,
she used her own life
force in its place.
She did?
[AQUARIUS] As far as opening
the gate, her gamble paid off.
But the toll it took on her
already waning health
caused her to develop severe
Magic Deficiency syndrome.
Grammie learned of this
several days later,
and traveled back to Ishgar.
Layla, my lady. I'm so sorry.
Can you find it in your
heart to forgive me?
Sweet Grammie, I don't
blame you for any of this.
Truly.
I appreciate all you've done
for me and my daughter,
but I'm not fit
to have this key.
Will you please take
it back, my lady?
I have no need for it.
I can't use Celestial
magic anymore.
Well then, surely you
can give it to Lucy.
She's obviously gifted.
I know she'll grow up to be
a great wizard like you.
Thankfully, my family's
duty to open the Eclipse
has ended with me.
I didn't want that
burden to fall on Lucy.
Now she's free...
to live her own life.
Which reminds me, I hope
Brandish is doing well.
[GRAMMIE]
Yes, she's a good girl.
She'll probably throw a tantrum
when she learns Aquarius
isn't coming back, though.
She and Lucy are around
the same age, right?
[GRAMMIE] Yes. I'd love
to bring her by sometime.
I think the two of them
could be good friends.
I think so, too.
[LAYLA]
Just like we are.
[GRAMMIE]
That's sweet, my lady,
but I'm just a humble servant.
[LAYLA] No, Grammie.
I consider you a friend.
[GRAMMIE]
Thank you, my lady.
--[thud]
--[gasps]
[BRANDISH]
Mom!
This is all because of you.
You're the reason...
she's dying.
Zordio, I...
Oh, God, no!
[gasps]
You're right. It really
is all my fault.
I deserve to be punished.
Yes, you do! You
could've saved her!
I'm begging you, Zordio.
Please. Spare my daughter.
My dear Brandish.
Promise you won't hurt her.
I'm willing to sacrifice
my own life to save hers.
It's my last wish.
[screams]
Oh, Mama!
I believe in my heart
that you and I can still be
great friends after all this.
Like our moms wanted.
There's something that we still
need to talk about before I--
Ya gotta help me!
What's wrong, Happy?
I don't know why,
but Natsu just stopped
moving all of a sudden!
Somebody has to
help him right now!
What's going on?
Certainly a lot of commotion!
[HAPPY] Natsu was in the
middle of fighting Zeref,
but then we had to pull back.
I was trying to keep him safe,
but the next thing I knew,
he just went limp and quiet.
Hey, Natsu! What's the matter?
Say something!
Hold on. What in the hell
are you doing here?
I don't have time
to explain it to you.
I can't even hear
his heart beating.
Natsu! Please don't die!
There's no way.
[PORLYUSICA]
Move it!
Of course he had to go off
and do something as
foolish as always.
He's been overtaxing his
magic power for years,
resulting in an
anti-Ether-nano tumor.
What does that mean?
A malignant mass is
growing inside his body.
And unless it's removed,
he'll soon be dead.
Can't we get somebody
to take it out?
Of all the healers in
Ishgar, none can do that.
[CANA]
Not even Wendy Or Shelia?
[PORLYUSICA]
I'm afraid it's impossible.
Then what are we gonna do?
[PORLYUSICA]
I'm sorry.
This can't be real.
Come on! Please say something!
Natsu.
[LUCY crying]
Hey, take these off.
Let me use my magic.
I can change the size
of anything I want.
So if I know the exact
location of his tumor,
I can make it small enough
that it never poses any risk.
You'd really do it?
If you can save him,
I'll do whatever you want!
[MAKAROV]
What a nightmare.
Leave it to Natsu to rush
out on some fool's errand
and come back in this condition!
Your crabbiness isn't
making things any better.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, huh?
I'm going to ignore
that comment.
Natsu will recover, all thanks
to that western girl's magic.
I never imagined we'd get
a helping hand from the enemy.
After this turn
of events, is she?
Until the war is over,
I can't answer that for sure.
Since I'm still your prisoner,
can you take me back to my cell?
Oh, it's chilly, so my
coat would be nice.
It's rather odd. Why would
she volunteer to go back?
That was so nice. Thank you.
Aye! Thank you for saving my
best friend's life, lady!
You didn't have to go right
back to your cell, you know.
[BRANDISH]
We're at war.
Keep being naive and
it's gonna get you killed.
Whatever happened in the past
doesn't change much for me.
I've no interest
in being your friend.
[AQUARIUS]
She just needs some time.
You haven't gone back yet.
[AQUARIUS] I'll be seeing
you again, Brandish.
Hear me?!
Yes, ma'am.
[AQUARIUS]
Tch.
[AQUARIUS] Anyway, I was
trying to tell you something
before all the drama.
[LUCY]
What is it?
Well, do you remember how I was
saying my key regenerated?
Yeah.
That means, now it's out
there somewhere in the world.
Maybe it's close by, in Ishgar,
or maybe all the
way in Alakitasia.
Or even some other
continent altogether.
But what's certain is
I can't give you any clues
as to where it is.
That's okay. I can't
lose a friend like you,
so I'll do whatever
it takes to find it.
Thanks, Lucy.
I'm actually kind of looking
forward to seeing you again
Plus, there's somethin' I
really wanna do when it's over.
Aye, Sir!
[LUCY]
Now I have something, too.
We can't afford to lose.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the battle
to liberate Hargeon continues.
And though the allied
forces of Lamia Scale
and Mermaid Heel
have fought bravely,
the ruthless Dimaria
and Wall divisions
of the invading Alvarez Army
have forced them to retreat.
[LYON] Their numbers
are too great for us.
At this point, we can't even get
anywhere close to the city.
I know.
But we have to take it back
to stave off the invasion.
Because if we don't,
they're going to keep on
sending ships full
of reinforcements.
[SHELIA]
We have to get the upper hand.
Aw, I wish Wendy were here.
Kagura. Are you okay?
What the--?
[SOLDIERS, WIZARDS gasping]
[KAGURA gasps]
Don't stare! Turn away!
Lookin' good.
[KAGURA growls]
You'll pay for this!
Right now, I'm not okay.
Poor thing.
[LISLIE] Get the hell away
from her, ya buncha creepers!
Jeez!
It's strange.
She shredded my clothes, but
she didn't even move a muscle.
We were a ways apart,
but she tore my kimono
to pieces in an instant.
Well, I'd be willing
to bet she was using
some kind of long-range
spell on you.
Yeah, maybe!
And like, her sword
could just be for show!
I can always tell when there's
aggression coming my way.
I can feel it.
So it's odd I didn't
sense it this time.
She was completely
motionless and calm.
That is weird.
Out of all of us, you're not the
type to let your guard down
and fall prey to a
sneak attack like that.
Well, then how do you
think it happened?
Her power is like nothing
I've experienced before.
I'm not sure what it is.
But it's dangerous
and unpredictable.
[NARRATOR]
In the snow-covered north,
Sabertooth and Blue Pegasus
have been pushed back
by the invaders from Alvarez,
led by the mysterious
and grim figure, Bloodman.
[STING] I've lost count of
the number of casualties.
I don't know if we can
handle this many troops.
I think it's really bad, too.
Even so, what other
choice do we have?
[YUKINO] Right, we have to keep
our front line strong,
or next thing you know,
they could be marching
right into Crocus.
Not to trivialize things,
but we don't want Sabertooth
to be the reason we lost.
Natsu'd never let
me live that down.
And I definitely do not wanna
be on Gajeel's bad side.
Help should be
arriving here shortly.
It's up to us.
We gotta hold things
together till they come!
Yeah, I think so, too!
[STING]
Enough mopin' around.
Let's show 'em what
Sabertooth is made of!
[NARRATOR]
And, to the east,
another battle has reached
its disastrous conclusion.
How lame!
You had a four-against-one
advantage
and this is the best
you old farts can do?
This does not bode well.
He took us down with
no help from the others.
I'm afraid going to Alvarez
has only made him stronger.
How can this be?
We've failed.
We've sullied the name of
the Four Emperors of Ishgar.
My old friend...
Sadly, I'll never see
your smiling face again.
Huh?
Sorry, Mavis.
I think turning you
into firewood
is going to be a lot
of fun, Warrod.
No joke. Time to
say God-bye-bye.
[WARROD]
Yuri... Precht...
...I'll be joining
you very soon.
[gasps]
[LUCY] In eastern Fiore,
God Serena singlehandedly
defeats the Four
Emperors of Ishgar,
bringing the battle
one step closer
to an unfavorable conclusion.
Meanwhile, Gajeel, Erza, Laxus,
and other brave Fairy
Tail members rush out
to lend their strength to our
allies on the front lines.
None of them can so much as
stop to catch their breath.
Next Time: "Not Until
the Battle is Over."
The fairies will continue
to race forward,
desperately fighting
to defend their home.