- HEY, GUYS.
READY FOR SOME
MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- ( laughter )
WAS THAT AN AWESOME JOB,
OR WHAT?
- WELL, THE CLIENT
SURE SEEMED TO THINK SO.
- FACE IT, YOU GUYS
ARE JUST LUCKY
THAT I DECIDED
TO COME ALONG.
- WE'RE LUCKY THAT YOU
BEGGED TO COME WITH US?
HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
- BECAUSE YOU WERE ABOUT
AS HELPFUL AS ONE
OF ERZA'S SUITCASES.
- YOU BETTER
WATCH YOUR MOUTH
OR I'LL PACK YOU
LIKE A SUITCASE, PAL.
- THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, BOYS.
NOW PLEASE GET DRESSED.
- FOR CRYING OUT LOUD!
WHY DOES THIS KEEP
HAPPENING TO ME?
- A BIT OF ADVICE, HERE, GRAY,
NEVER GET IN A FIGHT
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR CONVERSATION,
BUT...
- WHAT'S UP?
- WHEN I TOOK THIS JOB,
I WAS ORIGINALLY THINKING
IT'D BE MORE OF
A SOLO MISSION, YOU KNOW?
SO WHY'D Y'ALL
HAVE TO COME ALONG?
- AWW, COME ON,
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
- WE'RE FAIRY TAIL'S
STRONGEST TEAM,
SO WE GOT TO STICK TOGETHER.
- AYE, SIR.
- AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT.
- YEAH, WE ARE.
- NO JOB IS TOO TOUGH,
NOT FOR ME,
HAPPY, ERZA,
AND OLD DROOPY DRAWERS HERE.
- DON'T CALL ME THAT.
- HMM, WE ARE QUITE
A CAPABLE BUNCH.
- TRUE, THAT.
- YOU FORGOT ABOUT ME!
- LIGHTEN UP.
I'M JUST MESSING
WITH YOU, LOOPY.
- WELL, I DON'T APPRECIATE IT
AND THAT'S NOT MY NAME.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I TRULY DIDN'T MEAN
TO UPSET YOU.
I LET MYSELF
GET CARRIED AWAY.
IT WILL NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE,
YOU MAY STRIKE ME NOW.
- THAT'S OKAY.  I REALLY DON'T
THINK IT'S IN MY BEST INTEREST.
- Boys: SMART MOVE.
- ( gasps )
- ( whispers, murmurs )
- ARE THOSE FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS?
- I GUESS THEY DON'T KNOW YET.
- I FEEL SO BAD FOR THEM.
- WHY IS EVERYBODY
STARING AT US?
- IT'S NOT THE GOOD
KIND OF STARING.
- IT FEELS LIKE PITY.
( gasps )
WHAT?!
WHY DOES THE GUILD
LOOK SO BIZARRE?
- NO WAY.
- WHAT'S HAPPENED TO IT?
- NO, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- Happy: THE PHANTOM LORD.
- Natsu: OUR GUILD...
SOMEONE DID THIS
TO OUR GUILD!
- ( gasping )
- BUT WHO WOULD DO
SUCH A THING?
- IT WAS PHANTOM.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YOU MEAN PHANTOM DID THIS?
- Mirajane: WE COULDN'T
DO ANYTHING TO STOP THEM.
THEY GOT US GOOD.
- Narrator: THE BASEMENT OF
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD HALL,
WHILE NORMALLY USED
FOR STORAGE,
IT IS NOW A PLACE
FOR THE MEMBERS
TO NURSE THEIR
BROKEN SPIRITS.
- WE'VE NEVER BEEN
ON THE BEST TERMS
WITH THOSE PHANTOM JERKS,
BUT COME ON.
- WANT TO TEACH
THEM A LESSON?
- BACK OFF, YOU GUYS.
DON'T YOU THINK WE'RE IN
ENOUGH TROUBLE ALREADY?
- YO, WHAT'S UP, KIDS?
- UH, HI.
- SORRY WE WEREN'T HERE SOONER.
- WHY THE HECK ARE YOU ALL
JUST SITTING AROUND DOWN HERE?
- HOW'D IT GO, LUCY?
YOU FINISH THE JOB
LIKE A GOOD GIRL?
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- MASTER,
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
THE GRAVITY OF
THIS SITUATION?
- THE GUILD HALL HAS BEEN
COMPLETELY DESTROYED.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO GET
YOURSELVES ALL WORKED UP.
IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD
OR ANYTHING.
- WHAT?
- ( gulping )
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU
HOW COWARDLY THOSE DUNDERHEADS
IN THE PHANTOM LORD GUILD
REALLY ARE.
THEY STRUCK WHEN
NO ONE WAS HERE.
IS THAT ANYTHING
WORTH BRAGGING ABOUT?
- NOBODY WAS HERE?
- IT WAS AFTER EVERYONE HAD
ALREADY LEFT FOR THE NIGHT.
- I SUPPOSE WE CAN
BE THANKFUL FOR THAT.
AT LEAST NO ONE IN OUR GUILD
WAS HURT IN THE ATTACK.
- WE SHOULDN'T TROUBLE OURSELVES
WORRYING ABOUT PEOPLE
WHO DON'T EVEN HAVE THE GUTS
TO FACE US HEAD ON.
FORGET ABOUT THOSE FOOLS.
- AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN, GRAMPS!
WE CAN'T JUST LET THEM
TRASH OUR PLACE
AND GET AWAY WITH IT!
- I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THIS
ANY LONGER.
WE'LL HANDLE JOB REQUESTS
DOWN HERE
UNTIL THE UPSTAIRS
IS REPAIRED.
- WE SHOULDN'T BE WORRYING
ABOUT JOBS RIGHT NOW!
- NATSU! THAT'S ENOUGH
OUT OF YOU!
- AND YOU SPANKED ME BECAUSE?
- HANDS TO YOURSELF, MASTER.
- ( chuckles )
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING, OLD MAN?!
- AH, KEEP YOUR DRESS ON.
I GOT TO TAKE A LEAK.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY HE'S BEING LIKE THIS.
- Mirajane: LISTEN.
THIS IS JUST AS HARD ON HIM
AS IT IS ON YOU.
HE'S MAD, BUT CONFLICT
BETWEEN THE GUILDS
IS STRICTLY FORBIDDEN
BY THE COUNCIL.
- IT'S NOT FAIR!
THOSE PHANTOM CREEPS STARTED IT.
- I KNOW, BUT THAT
DOESN'T MATTER.
- ( grumbles )
JUST LET ME GO.
- Erza:
IF THE MASTER'S DECISION
IS TO NOT RETALIATE,
THEN WE MUST RESPECT IT.
- ( growls )
- WELL, THIS IS A PRETTY BIG
MESS WE'RE IN RIGHT NOW,
ISN'T IT, PLUE?
- WATCH OUT, BLONDIE.
YOU'RE ABOUT A STEP AWAY
FROM SWIMMING.
- I HAD NO IDEA
THE PHANTOM LORD GUILD
AND FAIRY TAIL HAD SUCH
A RIVALRY BETWEEN THEM.
- UH-HUH.
- HONESTLY, I THOUGHT ABOUT
JOINING THEM
BEFORE I MET UP
WITH NATSU.
THEY'VE GOT A REPUTATION
OF BEING
ALMOST AS CRAZY
AS FAIRY TAIL.
BUT I LOVE OUR GUILD.
I DON'T REGRET
MY DECISION AT ALL.
FAIRY TAIL IS KIND
OF LIKE MY FAMILY.
- VERY NICE PLACE YOU HAVE.
- WELCOME HOME.
- THEY LIKE TO SHOW UP
WITHOUT ASKING FIRST!
WHY ARE YOU HERE?!
- SINCE THE GUILD'S
BEEN ATTACKED,
WE CAN ASSUME THERE ARE
PHANTOM LORD MEMBERS IN TOWN.
- THEY'VE PROBABLY FOUND OUT
WHERE EVERYONE IN FAIRY TAIL
LIVES BY NOW.
- "WHERE WE LIVE"?
- MIRA SAID IT WOULD BE SAFER
IF WE HOLED UP TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, STRENGTH IN NUMBERS.
- I GUESS SHE'S RIGHT.
- THAT'S WHY EVERYBODY
IN FAIRY TAIL
IS HAVING
A SLUMBER PARTY TONIGHT.
- YOU ARE AN ATTRACTIVE
TEENAGE GIRL, AFTER ALL.
I WASN'T ENTIRELY COMFORTABLE
WITH YOU JUST BEING HERE ALONE
WITH NATSU AND GRAY.
I FELT I COULD ONLY RELAX
IF I STAYED HERE AS WELL.
- IT'S NOT TIME TO RELAX.
- SO IT WAS ALREADY DECIDED
THAT THESE TWO
WOULD STAY WITH ME?
WHY'D THEY HAVE TO
COME TO MY PLACE?
- WOW, YOU SURE HAVE A LOT
OF DIRTY CLOTHES.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET OUT OF MY STUFF!
YOU BETTER STOP THAT RIGHT NOW
OR YOU'RE BOTH DEAD MEAT!
- Natsu: HEY, PLUE,
DID YOU FIND SOMETHING TO EAT?
DON'T GO HOGGING IT ALL.
- Happy: LOOK, ERZA, I FOUND
SOME FRILLY PANTIES
YOU MIGHT LIKE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
YOU'D ACTUALLY WEAR
SOMETHING LIKE THIS, LUCY.
- I NEED TO GET SOME SHUT-EYE,
SO CAN YOU TRY
AND KEEP IT DOWN.
- YOU GUYS ARE TAKING THIS
"MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME" THING
A LITTLE TOO FAR.
- WE HAVE
A SERIOUS PROBLEM HERE.
YOU BOYS' HYGIENE.
I REFUSE TO SLEEP IN A ROOM
THAT REEKS OF SWEAT.
- I DON'T WANT TO TAKE A BATH
RIGHT NOW.
- BUT I ALREADY GOT INTO BED.
- COME ON, BOYS.
DO WE HAVE TO
TAKE A BATH TOGETHER
LIKE WE DID
WHEN WE WERE KIDS?
- WHAT KIND OF RELATIONSHIP
DO YOU GUYS HAVE?!
- THEY'RE THE STRONGEST TEAM.
- Lucy: MORE LIKE
THE STRANGEST TEAM.
- YOU SURE THIS IS OKAY?
- SHOULDN'T YOU STAY WITH LAKI
AND THE OTHERS
AT THE GIRLS' DORM?
- IT'S FINE.
I DON'T WANT TO
SPLIT UP OUR TEAM.
- THE THREE OF US
CAN FACE ANYTHING TOGETHER.
- I'LL ALWAYS PROTECT YOU.
- NO, I WILL.
- ( gasping )
- ( chews noisily )
- OKAY, NATSU, YOU'RE UP.
I'M ALL DONE WITH MY BATH.
- ( light snores )
- WANT TO TAKE HIS SPOT, GRAY?
- HMM?
- YOU SHOULD.
IT WAS SO RELAXING.
- GEEZ, I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALL
FEELING SO COMFORTABLE HERE.
- I SUPPOSE
I SHOULD GET DRESSED.
IS THIS A BIT MORE APPROPRIATE?
- IS THAT REALLY HOW
YOU CHANGE YOUR CLOTHES?
- THEN...
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHY PHANTOM ATTACKED US
OUT OF THE BLUE LIKE THAT?
- I'M AFRAID NOT.
WE HAVE HAD
OUR FAIR SHARE
OF SCUFFLES WITH
THEM IN THE PAST,
BUT NEVER ANYTHING ON THIS
SORT OF MAGNITUDE BEFORE.
- IF GRAMPS WASN'T
SO SCARED OF THEM,
WE COULD WIPE OUT
THOSE PUNKS ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- SINCE WHEN ARE YOU AWAKE?
- COME ON, YOU KNOW MASTER
ISN'T AFRAID OF THEM, NATSU.
YOU SEEM TO BE FORGETTING
HE'S ONE OF THE TEN
WIZARD SAINTS.
- I NEVER GAVE YOU PERMISSION
TO READ THAT. GIMME!
- YOU CAN'T SNATCH
IT OUT OF MY HANDS
WITHOUT AT LEAST TELLING ME
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT.
- YES, I CAN.
I PROMISED LEVY SHE'D BE
THE FIRST TO READ IT.
SO YOU'RE JUST
GONNA HAVE TO WAIT.
- HMM.
- YOU'RE NOT
GETTING IT EITHER!
SO WHAT'S WITH THESE
TEN WIZARD SAINTS, ANYWAY?
- IT'S AN HONOR BESTOWED
BY THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
AN EXTREMELY COVETED TITLE
SHARED BY THE TEN MOST POWERFUL
WIZARDS ON THE CONTINENT.
- Lucy: REALLY?
- Happy: PHANTOM LORD'S MASTER,
JOSE, IS ONE OF THEM TOO.
- THAT'S TRUE.
AND SO IS HE.
- HE IS AFRAID!
HE'S SCARED THAT PHANTOM
HAS TOO MANY MEMBERS
FOR US TO HANDLE.
- COULD YOU PLEASE
USE YOUR INSIDE VOICE?
- THAT IS NOT TRUE
AND YOU KNOW IT.
IT'S JUST LIKE MASTER
AND MIRA SAID BEFORE.
THE CONSEQUENCES OF US
GOING TO WAR WITH PHANTOM
ARE NOWHERE NEAR
WORTH THE FIGHT.
THE ORDER OF THE MAGICAL WORLD
IS AT STAKE HERE.
- BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY.
ARE THEY THAT STRONG?
- THEY AIN'T GOT NOTHING ON US?
WE COULD TAKE THOSE CLOWNS.
- NO, IF WE WERE
TO ENGAGE THEM IN BATTLE,
NEITHER GUILD WOULD SURVIVE.
THEIR STRENGTH EQUALS OURS.
PHANTOM'S MASTER, JOSE,
IS ALSO ONE OF
THE TEN WIZARD SAINTS.
WHICH MEANS HE'S ON PAR
WITH MAKAROV.
THEY ALSO HAVE AN ELITE
GROUP OF WIZARDS
SIMILAR TO OUR S-CLASS
KNOWN AS THE ELEMENT FOUR.
HOWEVER, THEIR BIGGEST THREAT
MAY BE "BLACK STEEL" GAJEEL.
I BELIEVE THAT HE'S MOST LIKELY
THE ONE BEHIND
THE GUILD HALL'S DESTRUCTION.
HE'S KNOWN AS
THE IRON DRAGON SLAYER.
- HE'S A DRAGON SLAYER TOO?
I THOUGHT NATSU
WAS THE ONLY ONE.
- ( scoffs )
- SO IF HE'S
THE IRON DRAGON SLAYER,
DOES THAT MEAN
HE EATS IRON?
- SO, GAJEEL, I HEARD
YOU MADE A MESS
OUT OF THE FAIRY TAIL
GUILD HALL.
OH, MAN, I WISH I COULD HAVE
SEEN THE LOOKS ON THEIR FACES.
THEY PROBABLY RAN AWAY
CRYING TO THEIR MOMMIES.
"BOOHOO, SOMEBODY BROKE
MY PLAYHOUSE."
( laughs )
- ( growls )
- ( screams )
- ( laughter )
- HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
I DON'T LIKE TO BE BOTHERED
WHILE I'M EATING.
AND BESIDES...
THOSE FAIRY TAIL CLOWNS
CAN'T CHALLENGE US.
WE'RE WAY MORE POWERFUL
THAN THEY COULD EVER HOPE TO BE.
- THE DIE HAS BEEN CAST.
I COMPLIMENT YOUR
EXCELLENT WORK, GAJEEL.
- I DIDN'T THINK WE WERE
HARD ENOUGH ON THEM.
SO I DECIDED TO LEAVE 'EM
A LITTLE SOMETHING EXTRA,
A PRESENT THAT'S SURE TO GET
THOSE FAIRY TAILER'S
PANTIES IN A KNOT.
- VERY GOOD, MY BOY.
BE SURE TO TAKE EXTRA CARE
THAT NO HARM
COMES TO THAT ONE
IF YOU PLEASE.
- ( laughs )
- Narrator: THE MAGNOLIA
SOUTHGATE PARK.
- ( gasps )
- Erza: EXCUSE US.
WE'RE FROM THEIR GUILD.
PLEASE LET US THROUGH.
- ( gasping )
- WHY ARE THEY STILL UP THERE?
- ( whispering )
- SOMEBODY GET THEM DOWN,
ALREADY.
- WHOA, DO YOU SEE
THAT MARK ON HER?
- WE BETTER NOT GET INVOLVED.
- LEVY!
- JET! DROY!
- PHANTOM LORD DID THIS!
- MASTER.
- I CAN TAKE OUR HEADQUARTERS
BEING REDUCED TO RUBBLE.
BUT I WILL NOT LET HARM
COME TO MY CHILDREN
WITHOUT TAKING REVENGE.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO TO WAR.
- Narrator: MAGNOLIA HOSPITAL,
A STATE-OF-THE-ART FACILITY
THAT IS EQUIPPED TO HANDLE
ANY SPECIAL CONCERNS
IN TREATING WIZARDS.
- Lucy: DROY, JET...
AND POOR LEVY.
PHANTOM LORD IS HEARTLESS.
HOW COULD THEY DO THIS?
- Levy: SO, LUCY.
I HEARD THAT YOU'RE
WRITING A NOVEL.
- UGH, SO THE WORD'S
GOTTEN AROUND ALREADY, HUH?
- WORD UP.
- I SHOULD'VE KNOWN
I COULDN'T TRUST THE CAT
AND THE PYRO
TO KEEP A SECRET.
- OH, I'M BEING RUDE.
I DIDN'T INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M LEVY MCGARDEN,
BUT JUST CALL ME LEVY.
- MY FRIEND
IN THE HAT IS JET.
- HEY, THERE.
- AND THAT'S DROY.
- OH, WOW, YOU'RE SO CUTE.
- AND TOGETHER....
- All: ...WE'RE THE AWESOME
TEAM SHADOW GEAR!
- OH, THAT'S COOL.
- ANYWAY, I'M A HORRIBLE
WRITER, MYSELF,
BUT I REALLY LOVE TO READ.
DO YOU THINK I COULD READ
YOUR NOVEL SOMETIME?
- WELL, I-- I DIDN'T REALLY
PLAN ON ANYBODY READING IT.
- WHAT? HOW COME?
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE POINT
OF WRITING A BOOK
THAT NO ONE'S
EVER GONNA READ?
- YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE SAY
THAT BEING A WRITER
IS LIKE SHOWING YOUR BUTT
TO THE WORLD.
- ( gasps )
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE EMBARRASSED.
- COME ON, LUCY,
PLEASE SHOW IT TO ME.
AND I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT YOUR BUTT,
SO DON'T GET WEIRD.
THE BOYS MIGHT WANT
TO SEE IT THOUGH.
- BUT I'M NOT EXACTLY
FINISHED WITH IT, YET.
- ALL RIGHT,
SO WHEN YOU ARE DONE,
I WANT TO BE
THE FIRST ONE TO READ IT.
- Past Lucy:
UH, SURE.
- Levy:
YAY, I CAN'T WAIT.
- Present Lucy:
AND JUST THE OTHER DAY,
SHE WORKED SO HARD
TO HELP US OUT.
WHAT THEY'VE DONE
IS UNFORGIVABLE.
THEY'RE GONNA PAY.
- Narrator:
OAK TOWN IS LOCATED
IN THE NORTHEAST CORNER
OF THE FIORE KINGDOM.
IT IS HOME TO MANY
HISTORIC BUILDINGS,
BUT TOWERING ABOVE THEM ALL
IS THIS MASSIVE
BRANCH OF
THE PHANTOM LORD GUILD.
- ( raucous noise )
- OH, YEAH! THAT'S PRICELESS!
- THOSE FAIRY CLOWNS GOT
WHAT THEY HAD COMING TO 'EM.
- I HEARD GAJEEL WENT AND TOOK
OUT THREE OF THEM, HIMSELF.
- ( muttering continues )
- THIS GUY HERE...
- I'M DRINKING THAT!
- ( laughter )
- OH, WE CAN'T LET HIM
HAVE ALL THE FUN.
- YEAH, WE NEED
TO TRY PICKING OFF
A COUPLE OF FAIRY WINGS
OURSELVES.
- ( laughs )
- ( groans, gasps )
- ( angry muttering )
- Makarov: FAIRY TAIL
HAS COME CALLING.
- All: ( battle cries )
- YA!
ALL RIGHT, WHO WANTS
TO PLAY WITH FIRE?!
- ( shouting )
- LET'S GET 'EM.
- PURPLE NET!
NOW WAKABA.
- ON IT.
HERE COMES SMOKE CRUSH.
- GUNS MAGIC!
THAT ONE'S MY SPARK SHOT.
- ( gasps )
- EAT THIS.
- VERY NICE SHOOTING, BISCA.
- GETTING A LITTLE
RUSTY THERE, AL.
LOCKED ON TARGET.
HOMING SHOT!
- HE'S A MONSTER.
- AND YOU DARED TO
LAY YOUR HANDS
ON THIS MONSTER'S CHILDREN!
WERE YOU FOOLISH
ENOUGH TO BELIEVE
HUMAN LAWS WOULD PROTECT YOU
FROM MY RAGE?
- ( frightened murmurs )
- HE'S SO POWERFUL.
- ALL THE MEMBERS
ARE STRONG TOO.
- YEAH, AND
THEY'RE TOTALLY NUTS.
- I DIDN'T KNOW FAIRY TAIL
WAS LIKE THIS.
- PICTO MAGIC!
WILD STAMPEDE!
- WOOD MAKE MAGIC...
DAM OF BASHFUL LOVE!
- WHAT THE HECK IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN, LADY?!
- LET'S GET THE CAT!
- PIECE OF CAKE.
- OH, YEAH?
- ( grunting )
- DON'T FORGET.
I'M A WIZARD TOO.
- ( grunting )
- YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH CATS?
- OF COURSE NOT, SIR.
- JOSE! SHOW YOURSELF!
- ( grunts )
TELL ME, WHERE CAN
I FIND GAJEEL
AND THE ELEMENT FOUR?!
- ( metal clinking )
- AHH, THE LEGEND HERSELF.
TITANIA ERZA.
I GUESS LAXUS AND MYSTOGAN
ARE TOO SCARED TO PLAY.
OR DO THEY NOT CARE?
EITHER WAY, MASTER JOSE
KNEW EXACTLY
HOW THIS WAS GONNA GO DOWN.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
PRETTY GOOD FIGHTERS...
FOR A BUNCH OF SCUMBAGS.
- UGH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE EVERYONE
JUST TOOK OFF WITHOUT ME.
BUT LEVY AND THE BOYS NEED
SOMEONE TO LOOK AFTER THEM.
SO I GUESS IT'S UP TO ME.
IT'S RAINING WHILE
THE SUN'S STILL OUT?
( gasps )
WHO ARE YOU?
- DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
JUVIA IS THE RAIN WOMAN.
IT'S ALWAYS WITH ME.
- UH...
- AND WHAT SORT OF WOMAN
ARE YOU, PRAY TELL?
- I'M JUST THE REGULAR KIND.
- DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
- WHAT'S WITH ALL
THE DRIP-DROPPING?
- PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
I'LL BE GOING NOW.
- WELL, TAKE THE RAIN WITH YOU!
- NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO,
( speaking French )
I BID YOU BONJOUR,
MADEMOISELLE.
- GREAT, ANOTHER WEIRDO?
- JUVIA, MA PETITE AMIE,
YOU MUSTN'T SHY AWAY FROM
THE TASK AT HAND.
- NO, MONSIEUR SOL.
- MY MONOCLE WHISPERS TO ME
MANY THINGS, MON CHERI.
IT TELLS ME THIS
BELLE DAME BEFORE US
IS OUR SOUGHT AFTER CIBLE.
- DOES IT?
SO SHE IS THE ONE.
- "CIBLE"? THAT MEANS TARGET.
- AH, PARDONNEZ-MOI.
I HAVE NOT
TOLD YOU MY NAME.
I AM SOL OF THE ELEMENT FOUR.
ALSO KNOWN AS
"SOL OF THE EARTH."
BUT IT'D BEHOOVE YOU TO CALL ME
"MONSIEUR SOL."
- I'VE HEARD OF
THE ELEMENT FOUR.
YOU'RE WITH PHANTOM!
( speaks French )
- CORRECT.
WE'VE BEEN SENT HERE
TO COLLECT YOU
AND BRING YOU BACK
TO THE GUILD WITH US AT ONCE.
MA BELLE COMPAGNE
IS A RAIN WOMAN
WHO'S ALSO PART
OF THE ELEMENT FOUR.
SHE'S KNOWN AS
"JUVIA OF THE GREAT SEA."
- YOU'RE THE ONES
WHO ATTACKED MY FRIENDS.
AREN'T YOU?!
( gargles )
- AU CONTRAIRE, MADEMOISELLE.
A REASONABLE GUESS, BUT WE ARE
NOT THE ONES TO BLAME.
THAT HONOR AND THE RENOVATION
OF YOUR GUILD HALL
WAS THE WORK
OF MONSIEUR GAJEEL.
ALTHOUGH, TO BE FAIR,
WE WERE WITH HIM IN SPIRIT
AS THE SAYING GOES.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?!
LET ME OUT OF HERE, NOW!
- DON'T WASTE YOUR ENERGY.
MY WATER LOCK SPELL
CANNOT BE BROKEN.
- AH, C'EST MAGNIFIQUE.
- DO NOT BE AFRAID.
WE HAVE EXPLICIT ORDERS
TO KEEP YOU ALIVE.
YOU ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN THE TARGET
FOR OUR RETRIEVAL MISSION
FROM THE MASTER,
LUCY HEARTFILIA.
- AH, VICTOIRE!
- THE TARGET HAS BEEN CAPTURED.
DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
- ( gasping )
- HOW DO YOU LIKE THIS?
- ( gasps )
- ( slurping )
AH HA.
OH, YEAH, NOW I'VE GOT
A FIRE IN MY BELLY.
- ( groaning )
- THAT CAN'T BE GOOD!
- HE JUST ATE FIRE.
- YOU DON'T THINK
THAT HE'S ONE OF THOSE?
- I'M GONNA BLOW YOU AWAY!
ROAR OF THE FIRE DRAGON!
ICE MAKE: LANCE!
- ( groans )
- WOOD MAKE MAGIC...
THE DISTANCE BETWEEN
THE TWO IS FOREVER!
- I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HECK
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, LADY!
- GUNS MAGIC, MAD SHOT!
- REQUIP!
MAGIC SHOTGUN.
WIDE SHOT!
- ( groaning )
( groaning )
- YOU'RE NOT DOING TOO BAD
FOR BEING A SNOWMAN.
- I COULD SAY THE SAME
ABOUT YOU, YOU PYRO.
- GOT 'EM RIGHT WHERE
WE WANT 'EM, DON'T WE?
- YOU BETCHA.
- ( groaning )
- ERZA!
I'LL LEAVE THE RABBLE TO YOU.
- YES, SIR!
- JOSE MUST BE LURKING
ON THE TOP FLOOR.
WHEN I FIND HIM,
THERE'LL BE HELL TO PAY.
- PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
- ( chuckles )
NOW THAT THEIR LITTLE
BOSS MAN'S OUT OF THE WAY,
IT'S ABOUT TIME I THROW MYSELF
INTO THE MIX.
( cackling )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- OH, MAN, WE TOTALLY
LEFT LUCY BEHIND.
DIDN'T WE?
- WE SURE DID.
AND I BET YOU SHE'S GONNA BE
PRETTY ANGRY AT US
WHEN WE GET BACK.
- OH! THAT'S GONNA BE
BAD NEWS FOR US.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
BRING HER A SOUVENIR.
- AYE, BUT KNOWING HER,
SHE'D PROBABLY RATHER
HAVE MONEY FOR BUYING FOOD
OR RENT OR SOMETHING.
- Both: NEXT TIME...
- Natsu: OH NO. I THINK
I JUST HEARD HER VOICE.
- UH-OH, SHE'S COMING TO GET US.
YOU BETTER HIDE
YOUR MONEY, NATSU.
- OH! I DON'T HAVE ANY!