[MAKAROV] What exactly does
this "Face" of yours do?
I understand that
this is a secret.
But no one's left to make use
of your knowledge but us.
Face is an anti-magic
pulse bomb.
This device can clear our
continent of any trace of magic.
A weapon that can
erase all magic?
That's horrible!
[gasps]
That would give Magic Deficiency
Syndrome to every wizard alive.
It gets even worse.
The demon that Natsu
fought told us that
Tartaros members use
curses instead of magic.
So, Face's activation would
wipe out every guild but theirs.
Every wizard who
stands against them
would find themselves
helpless and in agony.
What a deplorable weapon
your council has made.
[MICHELLO whimpers]
You tell me where
it is right now.
That thing never should've
existed in the first place!
I... I really don't know.
Please forgive me.
[MICHELLO]
From what I heard,
it was sealed away by three
former council members.
They did this by means
of body link magic.
I have no idea who
those members are.
Only the former chairman
can tell you that.
So, what the heck
is body link magic?
It's the kind that Brain used
to keep Zero sealed away.
So, all they gotta do is knock
off a few more council members,
and then they can
eliminate all magic?
Screw that!
[MAKAROV] We need to get
those three protected
as fast as we can. You said
that the former chairman
can tell us who they are, yes?
Yes. I'm all but certain.
[MAKAROV]
Drop everything else!
Find out where that
chairman lives!
We can assume that Tartaros
is looking for him as well.
Beat them!
We're on it, sir! We've
located the addresses
of 16 other former
council members.
We've got people from our guild,
and a couple others,
on the way to protect them.
Turns out that one
of those addresses
was the former chairman's!
Send someone to him,
as quickly as possible!
[LAKI]
One step ahead of you, sir.
They're already en route!
[LAKI] The two best
wizards we could send.
Hey, listen...
You know that Jellal is
one of their targets, too.
If you'd rather be guarding him,
I can handle the chairman.
For one thing, Jellal is
quite tough to track down.
Even if he is found,
he's more than capable
of defending himself.
I'll find him.
But our first priority is
protecting the chairman.
That's true.
His life is tied to that of
every wizard alive right now.
[CRAWFORD] I've gotten
to spend a lot more time
on my hobbies since retiring.
This chamomile is
fresh from my garden.
Thanks for sharing!
A lovely parf-- [coughs]
Smells lovely.
[CRAWFORD]
The ancients first tried it
because it smells of apples.
Excuse me. I realize
how rude this is to ask,
especially of such
esteemed guests,
but how did you locate my home?
I apologize for invading
your privacy, sir.
But as your life was in danger,
our guild put every resource
it had into finding you.
And then sent two
of its members to
my allegedly "secret"
doorstep without warning.
A letter might've sufficed.
[ERZA]
Sorry for the intrusion.
[CRAWFORD]
There's no need for that.
My days of scolding young
wizards are far in the past.
[laughs] Though I believe
I have seen you in court.
[gasps]
[FROG LAWYER]
The defendant, Erza Scarlet,
now stands before the court.
Eyewitness reports
have described
a heavily armored
female wizard who--
[FROG LAWYER grunts]
I am the all-powerful Erza!
[CRAWFORD sighs]
Just take them away.
I... I'm sorry about
this, your honor.
I can scarcely
bear the shame.
It's all in the past now.
I'm glad you're well.
I'd heard that your
guild spent seven years
in suspended
animation after that.
If I may sir, we have
some questions.
[CRAWFORD]
Yes, I'm sure you do.
You wish to know
about Face, correct?
[CRAWFORD] I was deeply
saddened to hear about
the demise of my
former colleagues.
Seeing as the Council,
itself is out of commission,
it is truly a blessing that
such noble-minded guilds
as your own remain to defend
us from this terrible threat.
Fairy Tail's first objective
is to destroy this Face
before Tartaros
can make use of it.
If you could tell us
where it's being kept,
that'd be a great help.
I'd like nothing more,
but I can't tell you
what I don't know.
Listen, sir...
[CRAWFORD] Perhaps you think
I'm unwilling to tell you
because this information
is classified. But truly,
not even I was informed
of the location of Face.
We've cause to think that
Tartaros already knows.
But if not even you were told,
then how could they?
[CRAWFORD]
Strange indeed. I wish I knew.
Yes, as do we.
But in lieu of that,
could you tell us the names of
the three former council members
who're connected to Face?
We will do everything in our
power to keep them safe.
I wasn't given access to
that knowledge either.
But why not?
This weapon, it could
devastate the entire world.
Thus, we sought to minimize
the number of people
who knew of its existence.
And told no one whose bodies
were made to seal it.
Not even the councilmen who
were picked for the task.
We hoped that these precautions
would help us protect Face.
So there's no way to know?
In that case, Tartaros
really will have to
slaughter every council member--
What? Something wrong?
It seems you have
a few more guests.
They've surrounded
the residence.
It sounds like...
...around twenty men.
[MIRAJANE] You should
find a safer room, sir.
[CRAWFORD]
It's Tartaros. Come to kill me!
You ready?
[MIRAJANE]
Mm.
[TARTAROS MINIONS]
Ahh!
[ERZA, MIRAJANE grunt]
[TARTAROS MINIONS scream]
You shall not harm
the ex-chairman.
I don't think we've ever
fought on the same side before.
There was Twilight Ogre.
But that was more
of a smack down.
[ELFMAN groaning]
Let her go! Don't do this!
Don't make me hurt my sister!
Lisanna!
I'll find a way to fix this,
just stay strong!
Make it stop! I'll do
anything! I beg you!
Beg me?
Begging implies that you've
nothing to offer in return,
but you do have something.
Something precious.
If her life is worth so much,
then I'll let you buy it,
with your soul!
They want a weapon.
One that makes Etherion
look like a cap gun.
Called Face.
At least that's what I've heard.
It has the power
to remove all magic
from the face of this continent.
[DORANBOLT]
I can't let that happen.
I will crush Tartaros.
No matter what it takes.
[COBRA sighs] There's nothin'
quite like the sound of freedom.
You know?
Really? Way to ruin the moment.
Cut him some slack,
he did get us out.
True. Thanks to your work,
we can enjoy this
lovely scene together.
You're my hero.
You've done quite well.
I never would've taken you for
such a shrewd negotiator, Cobra.
[laughs]
Long live the Oración Seis!
We shall-- Ahh!
[ALL gasp]
[BRAIN groans]
[COBRA]
I'm sorry, Midnight.
But it's time you realized,
Brain ain't who
he pretends to be.
All that fatherly
crap is just a lie.
We were never more than pawns.
You're right.
He violated our trust.
He had to be eliminated.
Sleep well, "father".
You brought us together.
That's the only thing
I'll thank you for.
So, now, we can do
whatever we want.
I could kill for a hot bath.
I plan to find out what's
become of my brother.
Go for it. But first,
we deal with this.
[DORANBOLT] They're in
your hands now, Jellal.
It's my debt to pay.
I'll do it in full.
[NATSU]
Huh?!
You're still hurt,
Natsu! Calm down!
You really should be resting.
[whimpering]
[NATSU]
Where's the old Chairman?
Spill it!
[MICHELLO whimpers]
Full speed!
[HAPPY]
Aye, sir!
[LUCY]
Wait a second!
[WENDY]
He never does.
[ERZA]
That the last of them?
[MIRAJANE]
Yeah. Nice work.
Rather odd though, isn't it?
That they went down this easily?
[ERZA]
Control of the former chairman
should be Tartaros'
top priority.
But these men are
ordinary soldiers.
Shouldn't they
have sent a demon?
[HAPPY]
What's this about, Natsu?
Man! How did I not
realize this before now?
No one, not even members
of the current council,
should've known where those
former councilmen were.
Or where this "Face" thing is!
So how the hell did
Tartaros find out?
[MIRAJANE]
Erza, I--
Something the matter?
[MIRAJANE]
I don't feel so...
Mira! U-Uh..
[NATSU] They didn't figure
this stuff out on their own.
Someone must've told 'em!
[HAPPY]
But who would do that?
[NATSU] I'm not sure, but
it must be someone powerful.
Someone high up in the Council.
I hope I'm wrong, but...
Just hurry! We've
gotta get to Erza!
[CRAWFORD]
Chairman Crawford reporting.
We need to move before my cover
is blown. I have prisoners too.
Well done, Former Chairman.
Could you bring them back
to the Guild Hall for me?
[NATSU]
That's the place, Happy!
[HAPPY]
Got it!
[NATSU]
We might be too late.
[foot steps]
Erza!
Mira!
No one's here.
[NATSU]
Yeah.
They haven't been gone long
though, I can smell 'em.
What could've happened to them?
[HAPPY] I don't smell Erza,
but I do smell burning herbs.
[NATSU]
There's something else.
[NATSU] Smells like
it's laced with some drug.
[HAPPY]
Like a knock-out drug?
You don't think they
got kidnapped, do you?
[NATSU]
Cowards!
Calm down!
The house didn't do it!
Plus, it belongs to that
big-shot former chairman!
It's the former chairman
who's been workin'
with Tartaros, Happy.
Then, he's the whole
reason we're in this mess!
Mira and Erza came to help him.
They didn't have a clue!
In that case, he probably
caught 'em by surprise.
[NATSU] Yeah, but
we're gonna find them.
[HAPPY] He must've burned those
herbs to throw us off his scent.
Nothin' stops a
Dragon Slayer's nose!
[ERZA gasps]
[KYOKA]
You've awoken. Good.
What is this?
[KYOKA] You're a captive
of Tartaros now.
What'd you do with Mira?
And the ex-chairman!
You took them too?
Crawford is ours all right,
but no one "took" him.
He's our comrade, you see?
And a surprisingly
useful one, at that.
It's all thanks to him
that we procured such
a fine specimen as you.
You're lying! The former
chairman would never betray us!
[KYOKA] Oh, but he would,
and he did. Struggle away.
Your shackles are infused
with bane particles.
So, good luck using
magic right now.
[ERZA]
Why isn't Mira here?!
What have you done with her?!
I've kept her alive.
Actually, I'm about
to improve her.
She'll make a fine slave
with a little work.
No!
Listen closely.
I need you to answer
a simple question.
Where is Jellal?
[ERZA gasps]
Fall back. This is my fight.
But there are five
of them! Let me help!
[JELLAL]
No. I'll handle this myself.
We've been underestimated
before, but this is just rude.
Arrogant's the word.
Well, that explains it.
You're Doranbolt's backup plan.
Come here to beat
us all senseless
and throw us back in prison?
I'm an escaped convict, myself.
I know better than that.
Yeah, we don't care what
you think you know.
We aren't giving up our freedom.
Try to take it and you die.
Aww. Surely, we can
work something out.
I only live for love.
What's the point of all this
violence? Let's be friends.
What's wrong with you?
It's like you're still sick
in the head from Nirvana.
Au contraire!
My head's not in charge.
No, I follow my heart,
and my heart has spoken!
I couldn't hurt that fine man
to save my life. Oh yeah!
After all I've done for you.
[MIDNIGHT]
Let it go.
Why should we?
We fought to gain freedom
and now we have it.
Richard's no exception to that.
It's his choice to fight or not.
My true name is Macbeth.
And I'll destroy whoever
would deny me my freedom.
Come.
Thought you'd never ask!
I was getting' kinda antsy!
Careful, Jellal!
You're a swift one, Sawyer.
Nobody uses that stupid name!
Your movements are blaring.
This'll shut you up!
[COBRA growling]
You're rather noisy,
yourself. Right, Erik?
[COBRA]
Uh!
[COBRA groans]
Come, my angels! Devour Jellal!
Eat every bit of him!
Let nothing remain!
It would seem that you've
acquired a new spell, Sorano.
[gasps]
He took them all out
with one attack?
This should be entertaining.
Like the good old days.
[KYOKA]
The chairman tells me that
you and Jellal are very close.
[ERZA gasps]
And? Why do you care?
Because I need to find him.
[ERZA groans]
I have this special curse I
only use for interrogations.
It makes a home in
your pain receptors.
Sets them to overdrive.
[ERZA groaning]
Speak.
[ERZA]
I wouldn't. Even if I knew.
[screams]
[gasping]
[KYOKA]
Our initial plan was
to hunt down every former
council member, one by one,
but now there's no need.
We've already found the names of
the three who've been
keeping Face sealed away.
Naturally, we've
disposed of the first two.
[ERZA gasping]
[KYOKA]
But the last eludes us.
You mean-- [gasps]
[JELLAL grunts]
[COBRA yells]
--[COBRA yells]
--[JELLAL groans]
[JELLAL groaning]
Don't do this!
[COBRA chuckles]
It took me a moment, but
I think I'm warmed up now.
[KYOKA]
The last seal is Jellal.
Once he dies, Face
will be unleashed.
That can't be.
[KYOKA]
Aww, did I say too much?
Chances are you'll never
tell me where he is now.
Even if you do know.
I don't!
Jellal and I haven't spoken
in a very long time!
[KYOKA]
Perhaps that's true.
But if you do know
and you tell me,
I'll let your comrade go free.
But if you don't...
[ERZA screams]
[ERZA panting]
Then, the both of you
will have to die.
I'm telling the truth.
I really don't know!
Let her go.
You can kill... me instead.
Please...
[KYOKA]
There's no hurry.
You have liters of blood to
lose before you have to decide.
[CRAWFORD]
How dare they vandalize
the home of their Chairman!
[FRANMALTH]
Yes, well technically,
you're their former Chairman.
[CRAWFORD]
I got a pension from the council
before I helped you destroy it.
Now, that's gone with my home!
Pension? You're about
to have more jewel
than even you could find
a way to spend. [laughs]
I suppose I can always say
that Tartaros destroyed it.
Make sure the firebug's
too dead to contradict me.
Then, they'll really
think I've been kidnapped.
Speaking of, how are
my prisoners?
[FRANMALTH] Lady Kyoka's
begun her torture process.
They'll have a gruesome
end, no doubt.
Make sure they die!
If those two were to
escape somehow and
speak of what I've done for you,
I'd lose my shot at
becoming Chairman again!
You can rest easy.
They aren't going anywhere.
And on top of that,
no one's ever gonna
find us in this place.
Say, what is that thing?
[FRANMALTH]
Uh? Uh...
[FRANMALTH laughs]
It's headed right for us!
[FRANMALTH screams]
You just said that no
one would find us here!
Well, no one's found us before!
Where the hell are my friends?!
[LUCY] Having located
Tartaros' headquarters,
Natsu launches
a one-man assault
in the hopes of rescuing
Erza and Mira.
Back at the Guild Hall,
the rest of us strive to
find out everything we can
about this new enemy.
As Jellal continues
his desperate battle
against the Oración Seis,
he reveals to them a secret
that they won't forget.
Next time, Tartaros Chapter:
Jellal vs. Oración Seis.
We've all spun our webs.
And when they collide,
there will be strife.