[DORIATE growling]
[NARRATOR] Doriate used
his regression magic
to weaken Natsu and Erza.
Ultimately, he battled Gray,
who made up for his loss
of strength with ingenuity,
while Doriate relied
on brute force.
[roaring]
[groaning]
[groaning continues]
[heartbeat]
[GRAY]
Wait... I know this feeling.
Can't be. There's no way!
[DORIATE growls]
I thought he was human, but...
This is getting old!
[ERZA grunts]
No! Why was I affected?
'Kay. Something's missing here.
Not cool.
[GRAY]
Could that be it?
Is it really that simple?
[BOTH]
Hold on!
[GRAY grunts]
Did ya have to wait
till the very last second?
[GRAY]
Yes! I was right after all!
[GRAY] I never gave
myself a chance to try!
Don't just stand there,
ugly! Let's do this!
[DORIATE roaring]
I'm lending you my body
for a spell! Don't let me down!
[GRAY yelling]
[DORIATE groaning]
[DORIATE yelling]
[DORIATE chuckles]
The netherworld gate
just busted wide open.
All thanks to you.
You'll realize the
consequences soon enough.
There's no turning back.
[trees cracking]
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
[CARLA, HAPPY] Oh, come on!
Can't we catch a break?
[NATSU]
Gray?
--[LUCY] Happy?
--[WENDY] Carla?
Run for it!
It's got an appetite!
--[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
--[GRAY, CARLA, HAPPY panting]
[screaming]
What... is that?!
I don't know, but it's hungry
and we're the next dish
on the menu!
Someone throw a spell already!
Turn around and ice it!
I can't afford to waste
magic power right now!
[NATSU] Why?
Because I think I found a way
to unfreeze the village
and get things back to normal!
[grunts]
Really?
Raven Tail?
What is she doing here?
Don't worry about her!
You really think
you can melt this ice?
I'm not a hundred
percent certain.
But I'm sure as hell
gonna try to!
All right then!
I can deal with the ugly bird,
while you melt that mountain!
Do that and we might
have a chance!
[GRAY] What?!
[NATSU] That's the Eternal
Flame! Can you do it?
Watch me.
[BOTH]
I'm countin' on ya! Go!
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
I'm all fired up!
[squawks]
It looks hungry.
I guess that demon guy
was just an appetizer.
Natsu!
Be careful!
If he eats me, I'll just
cook him from the inside!
[WINGED MONSTER squawks]
Way to go!
Not a bad kick.
[WINGED MONSTER squawks]
[NATSU groaning]
Natsu!
Don't worry about me!
I've got this.
You focus on the ice!
Get that fire to burn!!
[WINGED MONSTER squawks]
Save the Eternal Flame
and it'll save the village!
[WINGED MONSTER crying]
[WENDY gasps]
[FLARE] Uh...
[HAPPY gasps]
[CARLA gasps]
I'm all over it!
I haven't been able to do much
with the ice
around this village.
It's immune to my maker magic,
and I sure as hell
can't melt it.
The only thing that I can do
is channel it through my body.
I think that means this ice and
my ice have somethin' in common.
I'm lending you my body
for a spell! Don't let me down!
[GRAY yelling]
You're gonna channel that
cursed ice through your body?
I'm sure you'll handle it.
But what'll it let you do?
What I couldn't do before!
Once it's been inside me,
I think I'll be
able to diffuse it.
That's amazing. But are
you sure you can do it?
Won't know for sure until I try.
That's why I'm not usin'
this on the giants yet!
Step one is tryin' to suck
the ice outta this mountain.
I'm gonna give that giant
flame some room to breathe!
I'm not sure how this'll
play out. So get back!
[GRAY yelling]
[yelling continues]
Looks like the ice
is starting to evaporate!
Yes!
It's really melting! Yay!
No, it's sublimating, but still!
[giggles]
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
What happened?
Is there nothing left of it?
I totally believed we had this.
I didn't mean to--
[FLARE crying]
It's not real.
[WENDY gasps]
--[FLARE crying]
--[WENDY gasping]
[WENDY] I can feel something.
Some sort of magic power.
What could it be?
[gasping]
Without the Eternal Flame,
what can we do?
This isn't happening.
There's just no way!
This might not be
your fault, Gray,
it could have gone out
as soon as it was frozen!
[GRAY] No.
I screwed up.
Why didn't I try that
out on a house first?
Was I too cocky, or just
scared of gettin' showed up?
I'm useless.
[FLARE] Sacred Flame's
been strong for centuries.
I thought it was invincible.
If the flame is gone, then
what'll happen to the village?
It hasn't gone out!
[ALL gasp]
[WENDY] I'm sensing
residual thought energy!
Like I did with
Zirconis, but stronger!
What does this flame
have to do with that dragon?
[LUCY gasps]
Look, over there!
[GRAY] Hm?
Is something glowin'?
That's the center of the altar.
The mist is clearing!
It's lost a lot of weight,
but at least it's there.
For now at least, but it
doesn't look very healthy.
That's why Warrod needed Natsu!
If he gives it
some of his flame,
then I bet that it'll come
back stronger than ever!
Yeah, maybe you're right!
Did he beat that monster yet?
Natsu, hurry!
Yeah, yeah!
This shouldn't take too long!
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU yelps]
[screaming]
Oh no!
It got him!
[GRAY]
Keep runnin'!
[LUCY]
It's right behind us!
[ALL yelping]
[FLARE gasps]
That beam's gonna
hit one of the giants!
[NATSU grunts, roars]
[WINGED MONSTER cries]
I'll be outta your
hair in just a sec!
[NATSU yelling]
[WINGED MONSTER cries]
Fire Dragon Brilliant Flame!
[WINGED MONSTER squawks]
[BOTH whimpering]
[BOTH yelp]
[BOTH grunting]
The Eternal Flame!
[NATSU yelling]
Get back up, freak!
An earthquake?
That, or Natsu.
It's called overkill!
Heard of it?
[NATSU yelling]
[NATSU]
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Flame Lotus
Exploding Flame Blade!
[ALL yelping]
[gasps]
[FLARE gasps]
The Eternal Flame.
[cries]
Our guardian deity.
[FLARE]
You brought it back.
[BOTH gasp]
Yo, Happy! I wanna get
to the top of this thing,
do ya mind givin' me a lift?
Do I have to? It's scary.
This is where that
voice came from.
The voice and the thought
energy are one and the same!
That settles it.
[gasps]
The flame's been here for
centuries. Could it really be...
Hey there, Uncle,
how you been?
[ATLAS FLAME]
Well met, son of Igneel.
Aside from being
imprisoned in ice?
[ATLAS FLAME]
I've been good.
It's Atlas Flame.
Oh, yeah, from the Eclipse Gate.
That's the dragon that
helped us fight Rogue!
Oh.
But the Eclipse Gate
was destroyed,
sending the dragons
back to their time.
[ATLAS FLAME]
That's correct.
It sent us 400 years
into your past.
And all that time
I've burned on.
Didn't know you were still
alive! You must be ancient!
Yet you look so youthful.
[ATLAS FLAME] Ancient, yes.
But alive? No. Far from it.
Atlas Flame has been
dead for centuries.
I used my Milky Way spell
to give form to what
remained of him.
What?
[ATLAS FLAME]
I thought as much.
I don't recall dying,
but I do remember life.
And this isn't
what it felt like.
[GRAY] So, are you not
all there, or what?
[ATLAS FLAME] I don't have
the perspective to say.
But my memories
are clouded, muddled.
Who am I? What place is this?
I'd be forgetful too
at your age. Relax.
[ATLAS FLAME] You'd be dirt
at my age, son of Igneel.
Something seems off here.
Zirconis came from the same
era, but his memory was fine.
It might have
to do with the ice.
What about it?
[WENDY] A being does has to have
incredibly strong willpower
to leave residual
thought energy in its wake.
But the actual
magic power is weak.
Considering the strength
of the ice magic,
and the length of time
Atlas Flame was frozen,
it kinda makes sense that his
memories would be damaged.
[ATLAS FLAME]
Ice, yes. All around me.
[ATLAS FLAME] I didn't know
what cold was till then.
About that. Could ya tell us
how everything got like this?
Please, sir, I really
need to know.
You see, I used to live here.
[ATLAS FLAME grumbles]
[ATLAS FLAME]
His intentions were not evil,
but he mistook me
for something I am not.
Did you say "he"?
[ATLAS FLAME]
Yes.
A single human being transformed
this entire town into a tundra.
[BOTH gasp]
[LUCY gasps]
You're sayin' that all this
was done by one ice wizard?
I'd understand if it were
a guild, or a monster,
but not a lone wizard.
So... what did he
think you were?
[ATLAS FLAME]
He mistook me for a demon.
Not the first time that
mistake's been made.
But this man froze an entire
village just to get at me.
He was a Demon Slayer.
And a ruthless one at that.
A Demon Slayer?
First, there were Dragon
Slayers. And then God Slayers.
Just how many kinds are there?
Demon Slayer magic? I've never
even heard of that before.
To the best of my knowledge,
it's never been written about.
That explains it.
The ice hurt that demon guy
'cause it was made
by a Demon Slayer.
[GRAY] A man who uses ice like
mine to slay demons? Who is he?
[ATLAS FLAME sighs]
[ATLAS FLAME]
Everything's fading.
I can't remember. Who am I?
Our deity! You're the
guardian of this village!
Atlas, Flame of the Titans!
[ATLAS FLAME grumbles]
[FLARE]
Here my plea, I beg you!
Warm this village with
your light! Banish the ice!
Be the guardian you always were!
[FLARE crying]
[LUCY] Flare...
[FLARE]
I've no right to ask this.
[crying]
Please, save my family.
[ATLAS FLAME]
"Guardian," you said. Yes.
I was a dragon once,
but I died, and became
the Flame of the Titans.
[crying]
[ATLAS FLAME]
I created this village.
[NATSU]
You did? Nice!
Glad it's comin' back to ya!
[ATLAS FLAME]
It pains me to see it suffer so.
If I had a single drop
of moisture in me,
it would leak now from my eyes.
With what strength
of spirit I have left,
and the fire I received
from the son of Igneel,
I will burn this ice away.
[ATLAS FLAME] For I am more than
Atlas Flame, the Fire Dragon.
I am also Atlas,
Flame of the Titans!
Little help? Think you could
cool me off before I melt away?
That is one serious flame.
I can feel his spirit fading.
[CARLA gasps]
[ATLAS FLAME] Igneel.
The Dragon King Festival.
Acnologia. And Zeref.
I remember now.
I remember everything!
400 years ago,
your father fought
the strongest, most vile
demon in the Book of Zeref.
[NATSU gasps]
[ATLAS FLAME]
That monster's name is E.N.D.
And not even Igneel had
the strength to slay it.
[GIANT A] Huh?
What the--?
Why am I--?
That wave of heat.
It must've come
from the Eternal Flame.
Yeah.
The ice is gone? That can't be!
My friends're fast. Sorry.
[thud]
[GIANT G]
Mmm. Well, isn't this a sight.
A couple of humans have somehow
wandered into our village.
We'll settle this later.
[ERZA]
Minerva, wait!
Do try not to sound
so desperate.
I'll be back to finish you soon,
and on a finer stage
than this one.
You still have
time to stop this.
You're too strong to let
yourself be controlled
by the darkness.
No need to fret for me, Erza.
Darkness is coming, but I'll
be the one that controls it.
[ALL gasping]
The village. It thawed out!
Do the giants
seem bigger to you?
Yes.
Where's my uncle?
[cries]
[FLARE] Thank you
for sharing your warmth.
[BOTH grunting]
There's no trace left
of Atlas Flame.
He gave everything
to save the village.
To think that just a fragment of
his spirit could be so powerful.
He even created
a brand new Eternal Flame.
[crying]
So Igneel was tryin' to take
out a demon called E.N.D.?
Never heard of it.
I wonder what made
Atlas Flame think of that?
[HAPPY]
Who knows?
[GRAY]
An Ice Demon Slayer
paused dozens of lives
with just one spell.
[MESSENGER]
Excuse me, sir.
You've been ordered to return
to Headquarters
as soon as possible.
[MAN]
You go and tell headquarters
that I'm busy
paying my respects.
[MESSENGER]
My deepest apologies, sir.
But, each of the
Nine Demon Gates
have been summoned
to this meeting.
Forgive my insubordinace,
but, sir, I--
[MESSENGER] I'm begging you!
Obey the order, please!
[MAN] What's with
the trembling, friend?
Scared I'm gonna eat your soul?
[MESSENGER whimpers]
[chuckles]
You can put your fears to rest.
I only feast on
the souls of demons.
[LUCY]
Thanks to Atlas Flame's flame,
the Village of the Sun
is back to normal!
Well, maybe not normal,
but the giants can move now!
And they're
surprisingly friendly.
Having finished our quest,
we return to the Sequen
manor to collect our reward.
But with a guy like Warrod,
we should know better
than to think we'll get paid.
Or, at least not
in the usual way.
Next time:
"Song of the Fairies."
Some words are also promises.
Comrade means we're
in this together.