- HEY, GUYS, READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Cana:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Mira: BOTH ERZA AND MYSTOGAN
DECIDED TO CHALLENGE LAXUS
IN THE HOPES OF STOPPING
THE TURMOIL HE'S CAUSED.
BUT WHEN THINGS
TAKE AN UNEXPECTED TURN,
ERZA RUSHES OFF TO DESTROY
THE THUNDER PALACE ON HER OWN...
LEAVING NATSU AND LAXUS
IN A FACE OFF
OVER THE FATE OF THE GUILD.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( people chattering )
- HEY, WARREN!
WHERE IS HE?
DAMN.
- ( Mira speaking )
THAT'S 198.
199.
( panting )
THERE'S STILL NOT NEARLY ENOUGH
TO DESTROY THEM ALL...
AT ONCE.
( gasps, groans )
( panting )
I'M RUNNING LOW
ON MAGIC ENERGY.
AND I'M ALMOST
OUT OF TIME.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- LESS THAN A MINUTE,
30 SECONDS
UNTIL THE THUNDER PALACE
IS ACTIVATED.
YOU'RE TOO LATE, NATSU.
- OH, YEAH?!
WE'LL SEE!
( grunts )
- YOU... DOUBT ME?!
- AAH!
- ( laughs )
- ( groans )
I STILL NEED TO CONJURE
ANOTHER 100 SWORDS
TO DESTROY
ALL THE LACRIMAE.
- HEY, FAIRY TAILERS!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- THAT'S WARREN.
- THINGS AREN'T LOOKING
SO GOOD FOR US.
CHECK OUT
WHAT'S FLOATING IN THE SKY.
- HE'S USING
HIS TELEPATHY.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
PULL TOGETHER,
SO GET OFF YOUR BUTTS
AND LEND US A HAND.
- HMM?
IS THAT WARREN?
- WHAT'S IN THE SKY?
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE THOSE THINGS?
- IF ANY OF YOU
ARE STILL FIGHTING,
JUST GIVE IT A REST
FOR A SECOND.
- HOLD ON.
NOW I HEAR A MAN'S VOICE
INSIDE MY HEAD.
- WARREN'S USING
HIS TELEPATHY.
IT MUST BE IMPORTANT,
'CAUSE HE'S NEVER USED IT
TO CALL EVERYONE
LIKE THIS.
- NOW LISTEN CAREFULLY.
THOSE LACRIMAE UP THERE
ARE PART OF A SPELL
CALLED THE THUNDER PALACE.
LAXUS IS USING IT
TO THREATEN THE ENTIRE TOWN.
SO WE HAVE TO TAKE IT OUT
BEFORE HE CAN SET IT OFF.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME,
SO WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER.
- MAN, HE'S GOT ISSUES.
- BUT WHY?
WHY WOULD HE DO THIS?
- WAIT A MINUTE.
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT THE THUNDER PALACE,
WARREN?
- I'VE NEVER BEEN HAPPIER
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- Erza:
GRAY.  I SEE.
SO YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO TOLD HIM.
- YEAH.
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED SOONER,
BUT I HAD TO TRACK
THE GUY DOWN.
- Jet:
WAS THAT ERZA?
YOU MEAN SHE'S NOT
PETRIFIED ANYMORE?
WAIT, IF SHE'S BACK
TO NORMAL, THEN...
- WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER GIRLS?
HOW IS LEVY?
- Cana: THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY, BOYS.
ALL THE LADIES ARE FINE.
- EVEN JUVIA'S BACK
ON HER FEET.
- YEAH, AND SO IS BISCA.
HEAR THAT, ALZACK?
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
I WAS WORRIED.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS A GONER.
- THERE'S ONE PROBLEM.
MY TELEPATHY CAN'T REACH
ALL THE WAY TO THE GUILD HALL.
SO WE'LL HAVE TO MAKE DUE
WITH THE PEOPLE WHO CAN HEAR ME.
IF WE WORK TOGETHER,
WE CAN DO THIS!
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, WARREN!
WHY SHOULD I DO
WHAT YOU SAY
AFTER WHAT YOU DID TO ME?
- OH, UH, MAX...
HEY, I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I-- I SWEAR IT WASN'T
ANYTHING PERSONAL.
I WAS JUST DESPERATE
TO SAVE THE GIRLS.
- Droy: I GOT A BONE TO PICK
WITH YOU, ALZACK.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- YEAH, I CAN HEAR YOU.
I'M SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
- SORRY AIN'T GONNA CUT IT,
YOU LITTLE COWARD.
YOU SHOT ME WHEN
I WASN'T LOOKING!
- Macao: YOU BETTER WATCH
YOUR BACK, WAKABA!
- ( overlapping clamor )
- HMM...
- WOULD YOU IDIOTS
QUIT YELLING AT EACH OTHER?!
- All: HEY, SHUT UP!
PRACTICE WHAT YOU PREACH, GRAY!
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO BE GOOFING OFF!
WE GOTTA HURRY
AND TAKE DOWN THOSE LACRIMAE!
- ( overlapping arguing )
- SHUT UP!
- ( all slightly gasp )
- WE SHOULDN'T BE WASTING
OUR TIME ARGUING.
THE CITIZENS OF MAGNOLIA
ARE IN DANGER,
AND WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN HELP THEM.
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
WORK TOGETHER.
LOOK, I KNOW THINGS
HAVE BEEN ROUGH
WITH ALL OF US
FIGHTING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
BUT WE COULD DO ANYTHING
IF WE PULL TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GUYS
HAVE TAUGHT ME.
I KNOW THAT I'M STILL
FAIRLY NEW TO FAIRY TAIL,
BUT I PROMISE YOU...
I LOVE BEING
A PART OF THIS GUILD
JUST AS MUCH AS
THE REST OF YOU.
I ALWAYS DREAMED OF
JOINING FAIRY TAIL SOMEDAY.
IT'S WHAT I WANTED MORE
THAN ANYTHING IN THIS WORLD.
NOW THAT I'VE JOINED...
IT--
IT MEANS EVERYTHING TO ME.
IF YOU FEEL THE SAME WAY...
LET'S WORK AS A GUILD
AND SAVE OUR TOWN!
- LUCY...
- IF NONE OF YOU
ARE UP TO THE CHALLENGE,
THEN I'LL DO THIS ALONE.
I'LL DESTROY
THOSE THINGS MYSELF.
- ( all snicker softly )
- WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, GUYS?
YOU HEARD THE LADY.
YOU GONNA LET A NEWBIE
SHOW YOU UP LIKE THAT?
- Jet: SHE MAY NOT
HAVE BEEN A MEMBER
FOR AS LONG AS SOME OF US,
BUT SHE'S GOT MORE
FAIRY TAIL PRIDE
THAN ALL OF US
PUT TOGETHER.
- Alzack: RIGHT.
WE GOTTA SAVE THE TOWN.
WE CAN WORK OUT
OUR OTHER PROBLEMS LATER.
- Wakaba: JEEZ, NOW WE GOTTA
AGREE TO HELP,
OR WE'RE GONNA LOOK BAD, HUH?
- Macao:
YOU DONE GOOD, LUCY.
YOU GOT EVERYONE
TO COOL THEIR JETS.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
ARE YOU READY DO DO THIS?
- THANK YOU.
- THANK YOU, LUCY.
- Max: WARREN,
WE'LL WORK OUT OUR ISSUES
AFTER WE GET
THE JOB DONE.
- Wakaba: CAREFUL, MACAO.
AN OLD MAN LIKE YOU
CAN'T HANDLE ALL THIS ACTION.
- YOU CALLIN' ME OLD?
THAT'S RICH.
( laughs )
- ( sniffles )
RIGHT.  LET'S DO THIS.
- BUT THEY'VE GOT
THAT BODY LINK MAGIC!
IF WE ATTACK THEM, THEN WE'RE
JUST GONNA GET ATTACKED
RIGHT BACK.
AND IT'S GONNA HURT.
- WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO DEAL.
I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED UP
TO FAIRY TAIL, AND NOW...
I COULDN'T EVEN IMAGINE
MY LIFE WITHOUT IT.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH SO MUCH
IN SUCH A SHORT TIME.
AND NO MATTER WHAT, EVERYONE'S
ALWAYS BEEN THERE FOR ME.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE THIS IS
WHERE I'M MEANT TO BE.
IT'S MY HOME.
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
I'VE FINALLY FOUND
A PLACE WHERE I BELONG.
SO I'LL FIGHT.
'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA LOSE IT.
FAIRY TAIL'S MADE ME
WHO I AM TODAY--
A STRONG, CAPABLE WIZARD.
- MM.
I'M RIGHT WITH YOU!
- ( softly chuckles )
LET'S GO!
- AYE!  YOU GOT IT.
- I'LL TAKE THE 200
TO THE NORTH.
EVERYBODY ELSE
CAN TAKE THE REST.
WE CAN DO THIS!
- WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO MISS ANY OF THEM.
ICE MAKE LANCE.
( grunts )
- DEMON BLAST!
- NOW!
- ( grunts )
- HA!
- ( grunting )
-NOW GO FORTH,
MY SWORDS.
( grunts loudly )
- AAH!
- MAX SPEED ATTACK!
- WHOA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( all murmuring )
- ARE THOSE SOME KIND
OF FIREWORKS?
- LOOKS LIKE FAIRY TAIL
IS SPARING NO EXPENSE
FOR THE HARVEST FESTIVAL, HUH?
- ( townspeople chattering )
- WE SAVED THE TOWN.
- ( both scream )
- ( all scream )
- ( both groaning, screaming )
- AAH!
- HMM?
- Both: AAH!
- ( screaming continues )
- ( all groaning, coughing )
- YOU SEE?
- ( growls )
- TOLD YOU IT WOULDN'T WORK.
- ( all groaning )
- Erza:
IS EVERYBODY OKAY?
I CAN'T BELIEVE ALL OF YOU.
HOW COULD YOU DO
SOMETHING SO RECKLESS?
- WE SHOULD PROBABLY BE
ASKING YOU THE SAME THING.
- ( Erza chuckles )
WE REALLY DO MAKE
A GREAT GUILD, DON'T WE?
- Macao:
WE'D BE A LOT BETTER
IF LAXUS WOULD OUTGROW
HIS REBELLIOUS STAGE.
- ( Wakaba groans )
YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
- Droy: HEY, ALZACK,
YOU DOIN' ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, DROY, I'M FINE.
THANKS.
- WEREN'T YOU SAYING
SOMETHING ABOUT
OUR GUILD NEEDING A CHANGE?
THAT'S FUNNY. I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING THAT NEEDS CHANGING.
IT LOOKS LIKE EVERYBODY'S
GETTING ALONG JUST FINE TO ME.
HOW DO YOU EXPECT
TO BECOME OUR MASTER
IF YOU CAN'T GET ALONG
WITH THE REST OF US?
- ( growls )
AAH!
I'LL TAKE FAIRY TAIL
BY FORCE IF I HAVE TO.
WATCH ME!
IT'S MINE!
- ( chatter, laughter )
- LAXUS, YOU'VE GONE
TOO FAR THIS TIME.
YOU GOTTA STOP THIS
RIGHT NOW.
PLEASE.  WHILE YOUR
GRANDFATHER'S STILL ALIVE.
- I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
FOR YOU TO GIVE UP THE FIGHT!
YOU'RE NOT TAKING OVER
FAIRY TAIL!
'CAUSE I'M NEVER GONNA
LET THAT HAPPEN!
- OH, YEAH?
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU'RE MESSING WITH.
I'M A LOT STRONGER THAN
ANY OF YOU EVER DREAMED.
I COULD TAKE OVER THE GUILD
BY FORCE ANYTIME I WANT.
AND YOU'RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO STOP ME!
YOUR BEST BET IS TO JUST
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE JUST
BEGGING FOR SOMEONE
TO KNOCK YOU DOWN
A FEW NOTCHES.
I COULD DO THAT.
FIRE DRAGON...
IRON FIST!
( gasps )
- COME ON.
THAT ALL YOU GOT?!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
A WHOLE LOT BETTER THAN THAT.
I'VE GOT MORE POWER THAN YOU
IN MY LITTLE FINGER.
- ( both shout )
( grunting )
- ( groaning )
MAN, I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
HE'S SO STRONG.
- CAN YOU FEEL
THE ELECTRIC ENERGY
OF THE LIGHTNING
I'VE SUMMONED FORTH?
- WHAT THE HECK?
I CAN'T MOVE A MUSCLE.
- IT WILL PLUMMET
FROM THE HEAVENS,
AND TURN YOU INTO ASH!
RAGING BOLT!
AAH!
( laughs )
SO, WHO'S THE MOST POWERFUL
WIZARD IN OUR GUILD NOW?
( cackling )
GUESS YOU CAN'T REALLY
ANSWER THAT QUESTION
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN
TURNED TO DUST!
- THAT'S NO WAY TO TREAT
ONE OF YOUR COMRADES.
- ( exhales )
- ONLY A NUT JOB LIKE YOU
WOULD BE SO GIDDY
ABOUT TAKING DOWN
ONE OF HIS FRIENDS.
THANKFULLY, I GOT TO HIM
BEFORE YOU DID.
I WANNA BE THE ONE
TO TAKE THIS KID OUT.
- GAJEEL...
- I HAVE ANOTHER CHALLENGER?
( laughs )
- ( Natsu yelps )
- YOU'LL ALL END UP
DEAD SOON ANYWAY.
ANYBODY WHO DARES TO STAND
IN MY WAY WILL BE ELIMINATED!
- LET ME TAKE CARE
OF LAXUS, OKAY?
YOU STAY OUTTA THIS.
- NO DEAL.  I GOT A SCORE
TO SETTLE WITH THAT PUNK.
THIS GUY'S NOT MESSING AROUND.
HE'S A REAL MONSTER.
YOU CAN TELL HE'S GOT MAKAROV'S
BLOOD RUNNING THROUGH HIM.
IT SUCKS, BUT I THINK WE'RE
GONNA HAVE TO FIGHT HIM
AS A TEAM.
YOU AND ME.
- AIN'T NO WAY!
I'M GONNA TAKE DOWN LAXUS
ON MY OWN!
BESIDES, I'D NEVER TEAM UP
WITH A GOON LIKE YOU,
SO STAY OUTTA THIS!
- JUST LOOK AT HIM.
- HMM?
- IS THAT THE SAME GUY
YOU REMEMBER?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU SCARED?
YOU SHOULD BE.
( laughs )
- FAR AS I CAN TELL,
THAT'S AN ENEMY.
IF WE WANNA SAVE THE GUILD,
WE GOTTA STOP HIM
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
EVERYBODY ELSE HAS EITHER BEEN
KNOCKED OUT BY ANOTHER MEMBER,
OR ZAPPED
BY HIS THUNDER PALACE.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES LEFT
WHO CAN STOP HIM.
- SINCE WHEN ARE YOU
SO PRO-FAIRY TAIL?
- I COULD PROTECT OR DESTROY
WHATEVER THE HELL I WANT TO!
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID...
THAT THE SKY'S NOT
BIG ENOUGH FOR TWO DRAGONS.
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
BUT THERE AIN'T NO DRAGONS
FLYING IN THE SKY NOW.
NOT WITH ALL THIS LIGHTNING.
- JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR,
THIS IS GONNA BE THE ONLY TIME
I EVER TEAM UP WITH YOU.
- TRUST ME, THIS AIN'T FUN
FOR ME, EITHER.
WE'LL FIGHT IT OUT SOMEDAY.
- Both:
LET'S DO THIS!
- ( grunts )
- ( all grunting )
- USE YOUR BREATH!
- FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- IRON DRAGON CLUB!
IRON DRAGON SWORD!
AAH!
- ( laughs )
- FIRE DRAGON...
BRILLIANT FLAME!
- ( shouts )
IRON DRAGON LANCE!
DEMON LOGS!
- FIRE DRAGON...
- IRON DRAGON...
- Both: ROAR!
- DON'T TELL ME THAT'S THE BEST
THE TWO OF YOU CAN DO.
NEITHER OF YOU DESERVE
THE TITLE OF DRAGON SLAYER.
- WHAT THE HECK? HE DOESN'T
EVEN HAVE A SCRATCH ON HIM.
- BUT HOW?
I DON'T GET IT.
I KNOW HE'S STRONG AND ALL,
BUT WE WHIPPED OUT
A TON OF DRAGON-SLAYING MAGIC
ON HIM.
HOW'S HE STILL STANDING?
- I'LL LET YOU GUYS IN
ON A LITTLE SECRET.
I HAVEN'T TOLD ANYONE
ABOUT THIS,
'CAUSE I REALLY HATE
THE OLD MAN'S LECTURES,
BUT I GUESS I CAN TRUST
THE TWO OF YOU.
( roars )
( shouts )
- YOU GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME.
- OH, NO WAY.
- LIGHTNING DRAGON...
- I HAD NO IDEA THAT LAXUS
IS A DRAGON SLAYER TOO.
- ...ROAR!
- ( Natsu and Gajeel groaning )
- YOU'RE STILL ALIVE?
DAMN.  I WAS SURE
THAT WOULD FINISH YOU OFF.
WHY WON'T YOU JUST
KICK THE BUCKET ALREADY?
- ( Natsu straining )
I CAN'T MOVE.
- ME EITHER.
( groans )
- YOU TWO LOSERS.
ERZA AND MYSTOGAN.
THE OLD GEEZER.
THOSE WEAKLINGS
IN FAIRY TAIL...
AND THE PATHETIC PEOPLE
OF MAGNOLIA--
YOUR TIME IS OVER NOW!
- WHERE'S ALL THAT
MAGIC ENERGY COMING FROM?
- THIS FEELS FAMILIAR.
LIKE ONE OF GRAMPS' SPELLS.
- THIS GUY'S INSANE.
HE'S TRYING TO CAST MAKAROV'S
ULTIMATE JUDGMENT SPELL.
IT'LL TARGET ANYONE THE CASTER
SEES AS THEIR ENEMY.
- ( shouts )
- Gajeel: WE'RE AS GOOD AS DEAD.
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE RIGHT, METAL HEAD.
I'VE MASTERED
THE FAIRY LAW SPELL.
- THAT'S THE SAME SPELL
THAT DEFEATED MASTER JOSE.
NO.
- LAXUS, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- ( inhales, growls )
- DON'T DO THIS!
- ( growls )
- LAXUS, STOP!
- Natsu: LEVY?
- Gajeel: YOU IDIOT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- YOU'VE GOTTA SEE THE MASTER.
HE DOESN'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
MASTER MAKAROV--
I MEAN, YOUR GRANDFATHER...
IS CLOSE TO DEATH.
- ( both exhale )
- STOP THIS NOW!
GO SEE HIM ONE LAST TIME
PLEASE!  HURRY BEFORE
IT'S TOO LATE!
- NO.  IT CAN'T BE.
GRAMPS IS GONNA DIE?
NO WAY.
- PLEASE, LAXUS!
- THIS IS WORKING OUT
PERFECTLY FOR ME.
NOW THAT THE OLD MAN
IS AT DEATH'S DOOR,
I HAVE AN EVEN BETTER CHANCE
AT BECOMING
FAIRY TAIL'S NEW MASTER.
- ( gasps )
- DAMN YOU.
- THIS WILL BE THE DAWN
OF A NEW ERA FOR FAIRY TAIL.
I'LL REBUILD EVERYTHING
FROM THE GROUND UP.
I'LL FORM THE ULTIMATE GUILD.
ONE SO POWERFUL...
ALL WILL TREMBLE
IN OUR NAME!
- NO, LAXUS.
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
DON'T YOU EVEN CARE
ABOUT GRAMPS AT ALL?
- FAIRY LAW!
( grunts )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- NOT TO TOOT MY OWN HORN,
BUT I'M A VERY CHARMING CAT.
- HUH?  I DON'T GET WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, BUDDY.
- WE'RE DISCUSSING WHY
I SHOULD BE THE STAR
OF THE FANTASIA PARADE!
I MEAN, NOT ONLY AM I
OVERFLOWING WITH CUTENESS,
BUT I'M A WIZARD, I CAN FLY
AND I'M A TALKING CAT,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD!
BESIDES, I'M PRETTY MUCH
FAIRY TAIL'S UNOFFICIAL MASCOT.
SO IT WOULD ONLY MAKE SENSE
THAT I WOULD--
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- Happy:
WAY TO CUT ME OFF, NATSU!
- MY BAD. I WASN'T
PAYING ATTENTION.
WHAT WERE WE TALKING
ABOUT AGAIN?
- I WAS EXPLAINING WHY I WOULD
BE THE PERFECT CHOICE
TO BE THE STAR --
- UH-OH! WE'RE OUT OF TIME.