All I ever wanted is
the strength to protect those
I hold close to my heart.
I would give up all of
my strength if I could still
guarantee their safety.
It's strange but true.
[AZUMA]
What a shame.
You're quite interesting.
I had hoped we'd
have a fair fight.
[ERZA]
What do you mean by that?
We've reached a
different stage in our battle.
♪
[NATSU]
Previously, on Fairy Tail!
[NARRATOR] The battle on Tenrou
Island became a tug of war
of epic proportions.
Grimoire Heart gained the upper
hand at nearly every turn,
especially once Sub-commander
Bluenote Stinger arrived
on the battlefield.
When the Grand Spell Fairy
Glitter failed to stop him,
Fairy Tail's defeat
seemed certain.
But the tides turned
once more, as Freed, Bixlow,
and the powerhouse Gildarts came
back to aid their comrades.
So the tug of war continued.
But just when hope had
returned to our heroes,
a new calamity occurred
that could spell their doom.
Will the fall of the
Tenrou Tree be the instrument
of Fairy Tail's demise?
Or is there one last ray of
light in this abysmal darkness?
What gives.
What's happening to all of us?
I can barely move.
It feels like all my strength
got sucked out of me.
Yeah, and my head
is spinning in circles.
I may hurl.
I'd roll outta the way
if I were you Cana.
[LUCY]
You okay?
Cana?
Come on this isn't funny,
you have to get up!
I'm so tired.
My vision's blurry.
Is this some kind of spell?
Why is everything spinning?
I just ate some fish so
I know I'm not hungry but
I'm still dizzy.
I'm done for.
I can't go any further.
I think we're
all losing magic power.
There's no other way.
[GRAY]
That shaking.
Do you know what it was?
[ULTEAR]
Azuma.
[GRAY]
Oh man!
I feel so dizzy.
what the hell's going on?
It seems as though the
Tenrou Tree has been uprooted.
Now it will act as
a garrote for anyone who bears
the Fairy Tail emblem.
It's only a matter of time.
So you knew about this!
Was this your plan all along?
[ULTEAR]
It was an option.
Master Hades chose
to go with it.
And now I'm
aiding a fallen enemy.
What in the world
have you done to me!
[HAPPY]
Erza vs. Azuma!
[ERZA]
Why do I still stand?
[AZUMA] Since I control all the
magic power on this island.
I have kept yours intact.
Now, Titania.
All of your friends
are at death's door.
And you are the only one
who can save them.
You strive for the power
to protect those close to you.
Show me what that means!
[ERZA] Azuma of the
Seven Kin, correct?
And you're
acting under orders.
This is part
of Hades plan, yes.
Felling the tree was the easiest
way to deal a death blow
to Fairy Tail.
[ERZA]
I see.
If you could dispatch us so
easily, why keep me around?
[AZUMA]
You know why.
Now, are you going to give me
the fight I want or not?
Make your decision.
I don't really have
a choice in the matter, do I?
you insist on a fair fight,
so I expect you to return
our powers once you've lost.
[AZUMA]
You have my word.
Believe me I'm not fond
of these methods, either.
[AZUMA]
Of course.
You still have to win.
The lives of my
comrades hang in the balance.
I won't lose.
[ERZA]
Requip!
Heaven's Wheel!
Ready!
Scattered Petals!
Folium Sica!
Ramus Sica!
[AZUMA] Come on, Titania,
I'm not even sweating yet.
Get serious!
I'll force you if I have to!
That's better.
She must be using
her "Flight" Armor.
Okay!
[ERZA]
Adamantine Armor!
The impenetrable shield.
It's said it could stop
a direct blast from
a Jupiter focused magic cannon.
Excellent.
What do you say
we put it to the test!
[AZUMA]
The Thunder Empress Armor?
You're pulling out
all the stops.
I see.
You've truly earned
the name Titania.
Your requipping
speed is unmatched
and your sword
technique is flawless.
Very impressive.
You're everything
I wanted in an opponent.
[ERZA] His 'Arc of Trees'
is overwhelming.
This is bad.
[ERZA] It seems you're more than
just inflated ego and talk.
Your obsession with strength
is quite obvious now.
[AZUMA] Are you saying that
you'll fight me seriously?
Careful.
Getting what you want can be
detrimental to your health.
[AZUMA]
Her magic power's increased!
Even the Purgatory
Armor's magic power
isn't enough to defeat him.
[AZUMA] You overestimated your
armor's effectiveness and left
a weak spot wide open!
Tower Burst!
[ERZA]
Incredible.
I can't believe the amount
of power he wields.
I don't know how to counter him
My Armadura Fairy
armor is still broken,
and I seriously doubt any of my
remaining armor will do the job.
Think, Erza!
Well, there is that.
I may have bought the
seduction armor for private use.
but, perhaps.
I am not Lucy!
I have a warrior's pride!
[AZUMA]
What are you talking about?
[ERZA]
Come on.
Think this through.
If I'm going to overcome
his power, I'll have to
sacrifice defense and start
focusing on my attacks.
In fact, it might be
best to forgo defense entirely.
It's the only way.
I'll put all of my magic
power into my sword!
The blade that can't be
held without shedding all armor.
Come forth, Spectral Sword.
Crimson Blossom!
If I lose here, all of
Fairy Tail pays the price.
The fate of the guild
rests in my hands!
Yes!
Show me now!
[ERZA]
I can't afford to lose!
For the sake of my friends.
I'll end this
with one stroke.
Oh no!
You just
lost your chance.
Now face all the
power of Tenrou!
[ERZA]
I can't break free!
[AZUMA]
The outcry of the earth.
Terra Clamare!
The great Titania.
Finally falls.
Erza.
[NARRATOR] After Azuma
succeeded in uprooting
the Tenrou Tree, the
blessed protection magic
it was bestowing upon
the members of Fairy Tail,
swiftly vanished.
Suddenly, anyone bearing
the guild's emblem began
to lose their magic power.
With even Gildarts
and the Thunder Legion
out of commission, the fate of
Fairy Tail and Tenrou Island
now rests solely
on Erza's shoulders.
Alright.
We're getting nowhere fast.
Any luck?
Not here.
My magic power
is almost depleted.
But I can't figure out
what's causing me to lose it.
Stop the ride,
I wanna get off now.
This started after
that giant tree toppled over.
Do you think
there's a connection?
Yeah, maybe.
Whatever the reason is,
I don't think we're in
any position to fix it.
[HAPPY] Natsu, could you
carry me on your back
the rest of the way?
[NATSU] Sorry,
I've got a passenger.
And I'm afraid that he's
not lookin too good either.
This sucks.
Are we really stuck
here like this?
I hope it's just us.
If not, we're all
totally screwed.
What was that, Sir Siegrain?
I can barely hear you.
Jellal!
Or did that already
slip your feeble mind?
Siegrain is the fake name
he used when he was a member
of the Council.
Sorry, I guess
old habits die hard.
Look at him.
This is the guy who destroyed
our council building?
Cause to me, this dangerous
criminal looks more like
a caged stray dog.
[JELLAL]
Please hear my words.
[SERENA]
Whoa, do you...
Do you think he's trying
to cast a curse on us?
He couldn't cast
anything even if he wanted to.
As long as he's in here,
he's as weak as a newborn.
Wanna put him to the test?
What do you mean by that?
What'd I tell you?
He's nothing more than a
helpless animal in a cage.
Okay, you've had your fun.
Knock it off.
[NADARU]
I'm curious.
What were you mumbling
about just a moment ago?
Saying a prayer?
I just realized.
You probably haven't had
a decent meal since
you were brought here, have you?
Bet your stomach's
trying to eat itself.
Well, then.
If you say, "Please feed me,
Sir Nodaru" I might consider it.
Five little words and you'll be
feasting like a king in there.
That's enough.
[NADARU] However, if you don't
say it, I'll make sure the taste
of food becomes a bitter memory.
[NADARU]
Speak up.
[JELLAL]
Erza.
Don't give in.
You can do it, Erza.
What?
She lived!
That's impossible!
I hit her with all
of Tenrou's power!
[ERZA]
I heard Jellal's voice.
But how?
Was I just dreaming?
Stop it.
You don't have time
to be selfish.
Clear your head.
Don't cling to
phantoms and memories.
Now that you found
the strength to stand,
find what you need to win this.
[AZUMA]
Those eyes.
[ERZA]
I almost closed the distance.
Even if I get that close again,
I'm not sure I have enough
power to take him down.
But what I lack
in power, I make up for with
conviction and purpose.
Purpose he forced on me.
He's backed me into a corner,
and it'll be his downfall.
I will protect
what I hold dear.
The guild, my friends,
I will win for them...
I must!
It's been a long time
since I've feared an opponent!
[AZUMA]
Titania of Fairy Tail.
Miss Erza Scarlet.
You've fought bravely.
I won't forget your
name as long as I live.
I'm Not done!
How 'bout we
make your last name Scarlet?
That's perfect!
Now I'm never gonna
forget your name.
All I gotta do is think
about your pretty hair.
[ERZA]
No!
[JELLAL] It was
The color of your hair.
It won't end this way!
You don't have
a choice in the matter!
I win!
And there's nothing
you can do about it, Erza!
Terra Clamare!
No.
Erza.
[ERZA]
So this is it.
Death.
[NATSU] Don't tell
me you're giving up.
[ERZA]
Jellal?
We're here.
[ERZA]
My friends.
So that's it.
I understand.
Forgive me.
I've been such a fool.
I forgot the most
important thing of all.
I wasn't protecting
everyone around me.
[AZUMA]
Unbelievable.
[ERZA] They were the ones
protecting me all along.
Now I repay the favor!
[AZUMA] Tenrou Island's
magic power should be under
my control.
Yet it's supporting her!
Is this the strength
she was talking about?
The power to
protect those close to her.
It comes from
the bond they share.
What an amazing guild!
Well done.
♪
[HAPPY]
I can't find Gray.
You seen him?
[NATSU]
Actually, no.
Haven't seen Juvia
for a while either.
I wonder where they went.
[HAPPY]
Gray and Juvia?
You don't think.
[NATSU]
Oh you bet I do!
They're in loooove!
I wish I could show my love
to my snow white angel Carla!
Oh baby!
[NATSU] Alright, pal,
you're taking it too far.
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
Freezing Fighting Spirit!
[NATSU]
Wait a minute;
I thought Juvia was
wondering around with Erza.
[HAPPY]
Whoa, a secret affair!
[NATSU] Sounds like
Gray's got competition.