[SEILAH] You can do as I say, or
I can make you wrap your hand
around your sister's
throat again.
Your task shall be both
simple and unforgivable.
Return to your guild hall
and place this Lacrima
anywhere inside it.
Why? What will it do?
[SEILAH] It will emit a vast
amount of concentrated ether.
Imagine a Jupiter
Blast times 500.
Don't worry, your guild
mate's deaths will be swift.
I won't do it!
You can't make me!
Shall I have you kill
your sister, then?
[ELFMAN]
N-No.
[SEILAH] You've no choice.
My curse is absolute.
[LUMMY]
Speaking of things I don't like!
I think it's time I
transformed this one too!
Your name's Mira, right?
You and that stupid, cute face.
I'm gonna transform you
into the ugliest caterpillar
this world has ever seen.
What're you doing?
We're in crisis mode
here so you run away?
[ELFMAN gasps]
Is that some kind of Lacrima?
[gasps]
You can't stop me!
What do you think you're doing?
[ELFMAN]
Why did you have to come here?
Now I can't let you leave.
This is what I have to do!
[CANA]
Is it a bomb?
[ELFMAN]
This is goodbye.
This is the end for Fairy Tail!
[CANA]
Help!
Is he under some kind of spell?
What do I do?
Based on everything Happy
told me, I've done it.
[ALL gasp]
That's awesome, Levy!
So where are they?
Above us.
What?
They're right over us.
Are you certain?
[GAJEEL] What the heck
are you talkin' about, kid?
[LEVY]
I know how it sounds,
but when Happy escaped,
they were near the eastern
border, heading west.
Unless they changed directions,
they should be pretty much
on top of Magnolia now.
We'll see the fireworks soon.
Guess they thought
they'd come to us.
We'll have Natsu
back in no time.
Aye.
Prepare for war!
[FAIRY TAIL]
Yeah!
[HAPPY gasping]
What was that?
It came from Fairy Tail!
Their guild hall blew up!
[CITIZEN C]
Aw, and we only just fixed it.
[CITIZEN D] You don't think
this could have to do
with the Council bombing, do ya?
I really hope that everyone
made it out in time.
Let's hope so, 'cause nobody
could've survived that.
[CITIZEN F]
Uh. We should help 'em!
No way. If they're under attack,
it'll be too dangerous!
[SEILAH] The end of Fairy Tail,
delivered as promised.
[KYOKA] That was
quite well done, Seilah.
[laughing]
I can scarcely imagine
how many bodies must
be under that rubble!
[KYOKA] We've eliminated
Fairy Tail in a single move.
It would seem that
there was no need
for us to mobilize the Cube
against them after all.
It would.
Now that they're dealt with,
we can put all of our efforts
into activating Face.
The time is upon us.
The White Legacy: Face.
Rendered foolish by their fears,
the humans built the engine
of their own demise.
Once it has cleansed
this world of magic,
the humans will be powerless,
and then the age of
demons shall begin.
And all of this... is to prepare
for the return of Zeref.
Oh, that isn't good.
Is there something that
you'd like to tell us?
[FRANMALTH]
Yeah, the thing is
I'm picking up some
approaching magic signatures.
[SOLDIER A] Lady Kyoka!
Our sentries have spotted
three individuals
approaching the Cube.
Did you say three?
Well, that's off.
The Archive is detecting over
a hundred wizards en route.
[SOLDIER A]
I can't speak to that,
but we only saw three, sir.
This doesn't make sense.
[SEILAH] I'll put our ventral
surveillance onscreen.
What are those?
Cat attack!
Just cats?
Uh, don't you "just cats" me,
they're vicious animals!
[gasps]
[FRANMALTH] I see that you
let one escape, Lord Silver.
And you say that
these three creatures
are emitting hundreds
of signatures?
Look at their paws.
Each of them seems to be
carrying something.
Decks of cards?
[CANA]
Stop this, Elfman!
Think about what you're doing!
Fairy Tail must be destroyed!
I'll destroy you.
I'll destroy us all!
[CANA] Sorry. Hope you
don't take this personally.
[ELFMAN yelling]
Destroy. I must destroy!
That blonde, tan pretty boy
taught me that trick.
Always wanted to use it.
Crap. It's about to blow.
Damn it!
We'll have Natsu
back in no time.
Aye.
Prepare for war!
[FAIRY TAIL]
Yeah!
Card Dimension: All!
[HAPPY gasping]
[LUCY]
Huh?
Where am I?
Wait, this magic.
What the hell's going on?
Sorry, but I have to make
sure everyone gets out,
and some of you
are way too slow!
Is that you, Cana?
[FAIRY TAIL chattering]
Now then, I return
all cards to me!
[FAIRY TAIL yelping]
[CANA]
Happy! Carla! Lily!
The guild hall's
about to explode!
Get us out of here and
head for that Tartaros base!
Those cards they're
carrying must be stacked
with Fairy Tail wizards!
So it would seem.
Impossible.
I've failed my Lady Kyoka.
Establish a perimeter!
Deploy a gravity field
beneath the Cube!
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, ma'am!
[KYOKA]
Formation One battle stations
on all six of our sides!
[SOLDIER B]
Yes, ma'am!
Keep them away from the
top of the Cube at all costs!
[HAPPY yelping]
[CARLA]
What's happening?
It's pulling us in!
[ALL yelping]
[HAPPY]
This is gonna hurt!
Gravity. They've reversed it.
[CARLA gasps]
I always wondered what life
would look like upside down.
[CARLA] It's nothing you haven't
seen before. You can fly!
[HAPPY gasps]
Hello, Tartaros. I'd like
you to meet Fairy Tail!
Let's get 'em!
[FAIRY TAIL]
Yeah!
Fairy Tail! To battle!
What happened?
You back to normal yet, Elfman?
[ELFMAN]
What have I...?
What did I just do?
You wanna save Mira
and Lisanna, right?
Then pick yourself up.
It's gettin' kinda
noisy out there.
Whelp. Doesn't matter to me.
Here's what I'ma do first.
I'ma take that pretty face
of yours and screw it up!
How's it feel
having demon blood flow into
your pathetical human body?
You're gonna look
positively hideous
by the time my work is done,
and then none of the boys'll
like you more than me!
[LUMMY]
Ahh.
From beauty queen
to troll face.
Sure does suck to be you.
[yelps]
[LUMMY screams]
[LUMMY]
Hey! Not cool.
How did you even do that?
[whimpering]
[MIRAJANE]
I'm sorry.
I already have a bit of
demon blood in my veins.
That's how I'm able to
use Satan Soul magic.
[whimpering]
That injection was
really quite helpful.
[screaming]
[MIRAJANE chuckles]
I'm glad we have Erza here.
Hostages tend to be rather
effective against humans.
Sure took ya long enough!
How the tables have turned.
We had you in shackles.
How did you escape?
[NATSU] That'd be on account
of this awesome sword of yours.
[KYOKA]
You found the Heat Blade?
Whatever you call it,
it was exactly what we needed.
It practically fell
into our laps
when the place started shakin'.
Turns out it can cut through
just about anything.
What have you done with Erza?
[ERZA]
I received such tender treatment
when I was your prisoner.
It'd be a shame if I
couldn't return the favor.
I intend to make the
remainder of your short life
a living hell.
Makes you wonder what she did.
[NATSU] Where did you
take Elfman and Mira?
You mean they captured
Elfman as well?
[ERZA]
Answer him.
Whoever "Elfman" is,
I've not heard of him.
As for the one you call Mira,
two floors down, in the lab.
But there's no
guarantee she's alive.
What did you say?
I'm sorry, but
I need to find her!
Natsu, go help her out.
I'll take care of this one.
All right then!
What was the source
of all that shaking?
Our Fortress had a stronger
than expected reaction
to the unsealing of Face.
So, you did unseal Face?
Then, does that mean
you killed Jellal?
[KYOKA]
No. We did not.
We did break the seal, however.
After finding a
different method.
What exactly are you
trying to achieve?
[ERZA] Activating Face
would purge all magic
from this continent.
Why would you want that?
What would it
accomplish for you?
Everything we've done...
...we've done so that
we may return to Zeref.
What do you mean
"return" to him?
[KYOKA]
You're such a fool!
[KYOKA] These restraints are
designed to inhibit magic!
But they have no effect on
curses, thus no effect on me!
[KYOKA gasps]
So, you're all
followers of Zeref.
"Followers" would be
an understatement,
no we're more like his children.
We're all born of
the sacred books.
Born of the Books of Zeref!
It's only natural for us to
have faith in our Creator.
I have no problem
with faith in others.
But it can't justify what
the heart knows is wrong!
[KYOKA]
How could a human understand?
[ERZA] Humans have beliefs
of their own, and faith, too.
And we need that.
We mustn't let it blind us.
We think for ourselves,
and we stand for our beliefs.
[ERZA yelling]
[ERZA] You alone are responsible
for what you choose!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
They just keep on comin'.
I'm startin' to get bored!
Just who do you think you are?
Gettin' fresh with my Gray
while his back is turned!
[chuckles]
Ah, that is gross.
Taste my Iron Dragon
Roar!
[WENDY]
You asked for this.
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
I guess that didn't settle it.
Sky Dragon Roar!
Have a Lucy Kick!
[TAURUS]
Moo!
Heh?
Look out, Miss Lucy! Behind you!
[gasps]
I've got this. Regulus Impact!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Hey, thanks!
You show up on your own a lot.
Never lower your
guard in battle.
However...
[LUCY]
Uh.
I think you'd find
it quite rewarding
if you lowered it for me.
I've got my doubts about that,
but also, this isn't the time.
You've implied that
there may be a time,
and I am oh so willing to wait.
Loke! I could use
some help here!
Zenith of Regulus:
Lion Brilliance!
[MAKAROV]
Begone!
Knuckle Plant! Go!
[DROY yelping]
Falcon Soar!
I appreciate the backup, bro.
No prob,
but I think that weight you put
on might be slowin' ya down.
Ah, shut up! I already told ya,
it's obviously muscle mass!
Have you seen Levy?
She's got herself
covered. Take a look.
[LEVY]
Solid Script magic.
Stone Script!
[MAX]
Sand Rebellion!
Quit slackin' off, you two.
[DROY, JET]
We weren't.
[JET]
Just how many are there?
Too many to count.
Laxus and the Thunder Legion are
still down we gotta protect 'em.
Why did you bring
our injured with us?
Because if I hadn't, they'd be
in tiny little pieces right now.
[ELFMAN grunts]
[ELFMAN]
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
You call yourself a man,
so how about you quit sulking
and help us defeat our enemy!
I hear ya, yeah, a real man
owns up to his mistakes.
So that's what I'm gonna do!
I'm the Gunner! Yee-haw.
Dual wielded Gun Magic.
Tornado Shot!
Thanks, babe.
You all right?
[BISCA]
Yeah. Where's Asca?
Don't worry. She's with me.
This is fun!
I'm gettin' real sick
of you scumbags.
Rainbow Fire!
We can beat them back,
but how do we move forward?
[WAKABA] We gotta get on top
of this thing, somehow.
We could fly people over,
but this gravity field
is stronger than normal.
We're on the bottom of
this thing right now,
so that means we must be
real far from the top.
What do we do?
We're wasting our
strength down here
while Erza and the others
are lying in chains!
[yelling]
We have to find a way
to get into this fortress!
What the--?
An explosion?
It's Erza!
[MAKAROV]
There's our way through!
I'm coming, Mira! I'm
gonna save you, hold on!
[SOLDIER I]
I see them!
[SOLDIER J]
The escaped prisoners!
[SOLDIER K]
Run 'em down!
[NATSU]
Go on, Lisanna.
I've got this.
You sure?
Go save Mira!
Right!
[SOLDIER L]
Huh?
[yelling]
This is easy now
that I can use magic.
What's the deal?
They're all frozen in place.
[ZEREF] You've come
quite a long way, Natsu.
[ZEREF]
I always hoped you would.
[NATSU grunts]
[ZEREF] This is Tartaros,
the Library of Zeref.
Where all my books reside.
[LUCY]
Now that Erza's cleared the way.
Fairy Tail can finally
begin its counter attack.
But the demons of Tartaros
have already sown
the seeds of disaster.
And they fully
intend to harvest.
As the two mighty guilds
converge on one another
and engage in total war,
Zeref appears before
Natsu... just to talk?
What exactly is he after?
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
To Let Live or Die."
Truth runs deeper than darkness.