- HEY GUYS, READY FOR
SOME MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- Erza: PREVIOUSLY,
ON FAIRY TAIL.
- WHERE IS ERZA?
- Gray: WE WERE ENJOYING
A LITTLE GAMING AT THE CASINO
DURING OUR STAY
AT THE AKANE RESORT,
WHEN SOME OLD FRIENDS
OF ERZA'S SHOWED UP.
- SISTER, IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
AND THAT'S WHEN
THE TROUBLE BEGAN.
- Org: ARE YOU SAYING
THAT IT STILL EXISTS?
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- Leiji: ABOUT A DECADE AGO,
CONSTRUCTION BEGAN
ON THE R-SYSTEM,
A STRUCTURE DESIGNED BY
A CULT OF BLACK MAGIC USERS.
- Michello: BUT WE HAD ALL SEVEN
OF THOSE TOWERS DESTROYED.
THERE SHOULDN'T EVEN
BE ANY RUINS LEFT.
- EVIDENTLY THERE
WAS AN EIGHTH TOWER
THAT WE MISSED IN THE
WATERS NEAR KAH ELM.
- HOW DID WE MISS IT? IS THE
STRUCTURE CLOSE TO COMPLETION?
- I'M AFRAID I DON'T KNOW.
OUR TEAM MYSTERIOUSLY
WENT MISSING AFTER
SENDING THESE IMAGES.
- WELL, IT LOOKS FINISHED TO ME.
- BUT WHY WOULD THEY REVIVE THE
R-SYSTEM AFTER ALL THIS TIME?
- THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
IT'S NOT THE R-SYSTEM.
IT'S THE TOWER OF HEAVEN,
TO BE CLEAR.
- IT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE
WHAT IT'S CALLED.
IT UTILIZES FORBIDDEN MAGIC.
THERE WOULD BE CHAOS IF WORD
GOT OUT THAT IT EVEN EXISTED.
- WE'LL HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO SUBDUE THEM.
I SUGGEST WE DISPATCH
THE MILITARY.
- THAT'S NOT AN OPTION.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WE'D BE PUTTING
OUR SOLDIERS IN DANGER
BECAUSE WE DON'T KNOW
WHO WE'RE DEALING WITH HERE.
ACCORDING TO OUR
LATEST INTELLIGENCE,
THE BLACK MAGIC CULT
THOUGHT TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE R-SYSTEM IS NO
LONGER OCCUPYING THE TOWER.
- Michello: THEY'RE NOT?
JUST WHO IS THEN?
- IT'S A GROUP OF WIZARDS
APPARENTLY LED BY A
MAN NAMED JELLAL.
- JELLAL?
- BUT THAT'S THE NAME OF YOUR
TWIN BROTHER. RIGHT, SIEGRAIN?
- YES. UNFORTUNATELY.
THAT WOULD BE HIM.
- Happy: JELLAL.
- ( birds cawing )
- Lucy: I'M WORRIED ABOUT
THOSE PEOPLE WHO WERE
STUCK IN THE CARDS.
YOU THINK THEY'RE OKAY?
- Gray: WE LET THE MILITARY
KNOW ABOUT THEM BEFORE WE LEFT
SO I'M SURE THEY'LL BE FINE.
- I HOPE SO.
- WAIT A MINUTE,
WHERE IN THE HECK, ARE WE?
- Juvia: I DON'T KNOW.
WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING
SALAMANDER'S LEAD.
- NATSU, ARE YOU SURE WE'RE
GOING THE RIGHT DIRECTION?
- ( retching )
- MAN, WE'RE RELYING ON
YOUR SENSE OF SMELL.
PULL IT TOGETHER.
- HOW DARE YOU
DISAPPOINT MY LOVE
WITH YOUR CHILDISH ACTIONS.
- GEEZ.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW EASILY
THEY WERE ABLE TO KNOCK US OUT
AND KIDNAP ERZA AND
HAPPY. WE'RE PATHETIC.
- IN OUR DEFENSE, THEY MUST'VE
BEEN POWERFUL WIZARDS
TO BEAT ONE AS STRONG AS ERZA.
- WHAT? THEY DIDN'T BEAT HER.
QUIT TALKING LIKE YOU
KNOW HER 'CAUSE YOU DON'T.
- Juvia: ( sobbing )
UH, I'M SORRY.
- Lucy: CALM DOWN.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
THOSE GOONS THAT
ATTACKED US SAID
THEY WERE OLD FRIENDS OF
ERZA'S. WHICH MAKES ME WONDER
IF WE KNOW HER ANY
BETTER THAN JUVIA DOES.
- WHAT THE... I JUST
GOT A WEIRD FEELING.
- ( cawing )
- THE BIRDS.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING TO THEM?
NOT THE FISH TOO.
- Juvia: I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- THAT'S WRECKAGE FROM
A FIORE NAVAL SHIP.
- Lucy: OKAY, I'M CREEPED OUT.
- HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
- Lucy: IT MUST BE
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
- I'LL PROTECT US.
MY WATER DOME WILL KEEP US
FROM BEING SEEN.
- Lucy: NICE WORK, JUVIA.
- ( gasps )
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
IT'S BEEN COMPLETED?
- Sho: I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE SO SURPRISED.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING ON IT SINCE
YOU LEFT ALMOST TEN YEARS AGO.
- HAS IT BEEN THAT LONG?
IT'S AMAZING HOW MUCH
YOU'VE ALL CHANGED.
- Natsu: I CAN'T TAKE IT.
- Lucy: CHILL OUT,
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- Gray: THAT'S IT. NEXT TIME
WE GO SOMEWHERE,
WE'RE KNOCKING HIM OUT FIRST.
- Sho: THE CEREMONY WILL
TAKE PLACE LATER TONIGHT.
YOU'LL BE STAYING
HERE UNTIL THEN.
- CEREMONY? THEY'RE GOING
TO ACTIVATE THE R-SYSTEM?
- I'M SORRY, BUT THIS
IS THE PRICE OF BETRAYAL.
AND ALTHOUGH
YOU'VE HURT HIM,
JELLAL'S GIVEN YOU
A SPECIAL HONOR.
HE'S CHOSEN YOU TO BE THE
SACRIFICE FOR THE CEREMONY.
I'M SAD I WON'T EVER
GET TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO
HELP US GET TO HEAVEN.
AW, YOU'RE TREMBLING. ARE YOU
AFRAID OF BEING SACRIFICED?
OR DOES THIS CELL
BRING BACK MEMORIES?
- ( growling )
- Budi: DID YOU
BRATS REALLY THINK
YOU COULD GET AWAY THAT EASILY?
YOU'RE ALL GOING
TO BE PUNISHED BIG TIME
FOR TRYING TO PULL
ONE OVER ON US.
- NOW, NOW. NORMALLY
I'D AGREE WITH YOU
BUT WE CANNOT
AFFORD ANY MORE
CONSTRUCTION DELAYS
ON THE R-SYSTEM.
IF YOU TELL US WHO CAME UP
WITH YOUR ESCAPE PLAN,
WE'LL JUST TAKE
THEM AND LEAVE
THE REST OF YOU ALONE.
THAT'S PRETTY NICE OF US,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- SPEAK UP. WHICH ONE
OF YOU WAS IT?
- ( sobbing )
- I WAS...
- IT WAS ME.
I CAME UP WITH OUR ESCAPE
PLAN. IT WAS ALL ME.
- OH?
- WELL, AREN'T YOU BRAVE.
BUT I KNOW IT WASN'T YOU.
IT WAS THE REDHEAD.
- Budi: TAKE HER AWAY.
- NO, IT WASN'T HER.
I SWEAR IT WAS MY IDEA.
SHE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- YEAH, LET HER GO.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- ( both screams )
- PLEASE DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME
'CAUSE I'LL BE OKAY.
- ERZA.
- IT'S JUST LIKE
YOU SAID, JELLAL.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF.
- ERZA.
THEY WON'T GET
AWAY WITH THIS.
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
ENDED UP BEING PUNISHED
EVEN THOUGH I CAME
UP WITH THE PLAN,
BUT I WAS TOO SCARED
TO SAY ANYTHING.
I'M SORRY. IT WAS MY FAULT.
- THAT'S IN THE PAST, SHO.
RIGHT NOW, I'M WORRIED
THAT NONE OF YOU REALIZE
HOW DANGEROUS IT IS TO
RESURRECT SOMEONE
USING THE R-SYSTEM.
- WOW. I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO KNOW WHAT IT'S PURPOSE WAS.
THAT'S QUITE A SURPRISE.
- THE "REVIVE SYSTEM".
IN EXCHANGE FOR
COUNTLESS SACRIFICES,
BRINGS A SINGLE PERSON
BACK FROM THE DEAD.
IT IS INHUMANE,
FORBIDDEN, BLACK MAGIC.
- SURE IT'S FORBIDDEN
BUT WHOEVER SAID MAGIC
HAD TO BE HUMANE?
I HAPPEN TO BELIEVE MAGIC
WEARS AWAY AT ONE'S HUMANITY.
- THAT'S A BLACK
MAGIC PHILOSOPHY.
ARE YOU ONE OF THEM NOW?
- ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
COMPARING US TO THOSE IDIOTS?
THEY THOUGHT THIS TOWER
WAS ONLY GOOD FOR
RESURRECTION MAGIC.
WE KNOW BETTER 'CAUSE
WE'VE BEEN ENLIGHTENED.
JELLAL TOLD US THAT HE CAN USE
THE TOWER TO GET US INTO HEAVEN.
- TO HEAVEN?
- YOU SEE, ONCE WE USE
THE R-SYSTEM TO REVIVE HIM,
THE WORLD WILL BE REBORN.
AND WE WILL BECOME IT'S RULERS.
THE CULT MEMBERS WHO KEPT US
PRISONER FOR ALL THOSE YEARS,
THE LOVED ONES OF THE SISTER
WHO BETRAYED US,
THE CITIZENS WHO LIVE
THEIR ENTIRE LIVES
BLISSFULLY IGNORANT,
THOSE FOOLS ON
THE MAGIC COUNCIL,
WE'RE GOING TO PUT
FEAR AND SORROW
IN THE HEARTS OF EVERY
LAST ONE OF THEM.
THEY'LL BE STRIPPED OF THEIR
FREEDOM AND DENIED ANY RIGHTS
ONCE WE'RE IN CONTROL.
THEY'LL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO BOW DOWN BEFORE US.
( laughs )
- SHO.
- ( chuckling )
- WHAT COULD'VE POSSIBLY CAUSED
YOU TO CHANGE SO DRASTICALLY?
JELLAL. WHAT HAS
HE DONE TO THEM?
- ( exclaims )
I'M TOTALLY SURROUNDED
BY KITTY CATS.
WHOA, WHERE AM I? CREEPY.
- MEOW.
- A CREEPY CAT GIRL.
- SO, HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
- WELL, I'VE BEEN BETTER.
- ( exclaims )
I'VE GOT A TALKING KITTY.
YOU'RE GOING TO HUG
ME TO DEATH.
- MILLI, DOLL. BETTER LET GO
BEFORE YOU KNOCK OFF THAT CAT.
- MEOW.
- IT'S YOU.
- SURE, A TALKING CAT IS DANDY.
KNOW WHAT'S DANDIER?
- A CAT THAT CAN TALK.
- OH, YEAH.
- BUT THAT'S THE SAME THING.
HOW'D I END UP IN THIS PLACE?
AND WHAT HAPPENED TO NATSU?
- DON'T GET MOUTHY,
OR YOU'LL END UP
SIX FEET UNDER
JUST LIKE YOUR
LITTLE PINK FRIEND.
- THERE'S NO WAY THIS GUY
COULD HAVE TAKEN DOWN NATSU.
- WE GOT BAD NEWS.
- ERZA SCARLET HAS
ESCAPED HER CELL.
- SHE DID? THAT'S ERZY FOR YOU.
- WELL, THERE IS NO WAY
THE BROAD'S BUSTING OUT
OF THIS TOWER AGAIN.
- PLEASE, FOLLOW US.
- ERZA'S HERE.
THEY GOT HER, TOO.
- ( Jellal laughing )
- MASTER JELLAL?
- LITTLE ERZA'S GROWN
INTO AN AMAZING WOMAN.
I MUST SAY, I'M IMPRESSED.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HOW THIS
ALL PLAYS OUT. WILL I PREVAIL?
OR WILL IT BE HER?
WE'LL HAVE A GAME THAT
INTERWEAVES PAST AND FUTURE,
LIFE AND DEATH.
- Michello: WE MUST DO
SOMETHING TO STOP JELLAL.
- Leiji: WE SHOULD
GATHER INFORMATION,
- Belno: DISPATCH THE MILITARY.
- YOU IGNORANT FOOLS.
- Leiji: SIEGRAIN.
- Belno: HOW DARE YOU?
- ONLY FOOLS WOULD
SEND IN THE MILITARY
AND RISK THE LIVES OF HUNDREDS
OF INNOCENT SOLDIERS.
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT'S FAR TOO DANGEROUS.
WHAT DO YOU PROPOSE WE DO?
- THIS IS A PRECARIOUS
SITUATION.
IF WE WANT TO STOP HIM,
WE'LL HAVE TO COMPLETELY
DESTROY THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
AND THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY TO DO THAT.
ETHERION.
- ARE YOU INSANE?
- THAT'S CROSS-DIMENSIONAL
DESTRUCTION MAGIC.
- WE CAN'T.
- DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
DEVASTATION IT WOULD CAUSE?
THAT WEAPON HAS THE POWER
TO OBLITERATE AN ENTIRE NATION.
- Belno: ETHERION IS
AN ABSOLUTE LAST RESORT.
IT IS MORE DANGEROUS
THAN THE R-SYSTEM ITSELF.
- Siegrain: JUST HEAR ME OUT.
THE SATELLITE SQUARE
CAN PINPOINT A TARGET
ANYWHERE IN THE REGION.
IF WE FOCUS IT
DIRECTLY ON THE TOWER,
WE CAN CAUSE LESS
COLLATERAL DAMAGE
AND DESTROY
THE STRUCTURE.
- I VOTE TO FIRE.
- NOT YOU TOO.
HAVE YOU GONE MAD?
- THREE MORE IN FAVOR
WILL GIVE US THE MAJORITY.
BUT WE CAN'T LET
DELIBERATIONS DELAY US,
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
I URGE YOU TO
VOTE WITH ME.
WE CANNOT ALLOW JELLAL TO
ACTIVATE THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
- BUT ALONG WITH
DESTROYING THE TOWER,
AN ETHERION BLAST WILL
NO DOUBT KILL YOUR BROTHER.
- I REALIZE THAT.
HOWEVER, IT'S A SACRIFICE
THAT MUST BE MADE.
- TALK. TELL ME WHERE
I CAN FIND JELLAL.
-THEY GOT A TON OF LOOKOUTS.
- LET'S CHARGE THEM.
- Lucy: DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
REMEMBER, THEY HAVE
ERZA AND HAPPY.
IF WE SCREW THIS UP, WE COULD
BE PUTTING THEM IN DANGER.
- MAN, THIS IS GOING
TO BE TRICKY.
- I FOUND AN UNDERWATER
PASSAGEWAY INTO THE TOWER.
- SERIOUSLY? WAY TO GO.
- YOU HEAR THAT, LUCY?
I WAS JUST PRAISED
BY GRAY, NOT YOU.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- Juvia: WE CAN SWIM
THERE IN TEN MINUTES.
- Natsu: WE CAN HOLD
OUR BREATH THAT LONG, RIGHT?
- Gray: PROBABLY.
- THAT'S NOT  HUMANLY
POSSIBLE, YOU DOPES.
- IN THAT CASE, I SUGGEST
YOU WEAR THESE.
IT'S A WATER SHELL
CONTAINING OXYGEN.
THIS WAY YOU CAN BREATHE
WHILE UNDERWATER.
- WOW, YOU'RE AWESOME.
AND WHO ARE YOU AGAIN?
- Gray: SO, WE'RE BENEATH
THE TOWER NOW, HUH?
- I WONDER WHERE THEY'RE
KEEPING ERZA AND HAPPY.
- THEY MAY LOOK SILLY
BUT THEY SURE DO WORK.
- I'M IMPRESSED
YOU MADE IT HERE
BECAUSE I PURPOSELY
MADE YOUR SHELL SMALLER
SO YOU'D HAVE
TROUBLE BREATHING.
- GEE, THANKS.
- ( growls )
- INTRUDERS.
- Lucy: UH, OH.
- IDENTIFY YOURSELVES.
- GUESS WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
WE'RE HAVE TO FIGHT THEM.
- YES.
- YOU LOSERS WANT
TO KNOW WHO WE ARE?
WE'RE THE WIZARDS WHO'RE
GOING TO POUND YOUR FACES IN.
- WHAT THE...
- WE'RE FROM FAIRY TAIL.
- OW, SO HOT.
- OKAY, ICE MAKE LANCE.
- SO COLD.
- OH, WOW. SHE'S
FIGHTING IN HER BIKINI.
- OPEN GATE OF THE MAIDEN.
VIRGO.
- DID YOU SUMMON ME, PRINCESS?
- IT'S A MAID. SHE'S WAY
HOTTER THAN BIKINI GIRL.
- THESE PERVS NEED
TO BE PUNISHED.
- AS YOU WISH.
- IT'S LIKE SHE'S
MADE OF WATER.
- CAREFUL MEN, BLADES
WON'T AFFECT HER.
- BUT I BET OUR GUNS WILL.
- WHOA. WHAT'S WITH THIS CHICK?
- DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
WATER SLICER.
THAT SEEMS TO HAVE DONE THE JOB.
- Gary: GOOD WORK, TEAM.
- I HOPE WE'RE NOT
CALLING ATTENTION TO, AW,
WHO AM I KIDDING?
- Virgo: I'M AFRAID SO, MISS.
- SO WHERE'S THE
BLOCKHEAD, BUDDY?
- Natsu: WHAT'S THAT?
- I THINK IT'S THEIR WAY
OF SAYING, COME ON IN.
- MASTER, WHY ARE YOU INVITING
THEM INTO THE TOWER?
- AS I SAID BEFORE,
THIS IS ALL ONE BIG GAME.
THEY WERE LUCKY ENOUGH
TO CLEAR THE FIRST STAGE,
BUT THEY STILL
HAVE A WAYS TO GO.
I'M JUST TRYING TO MAKE
THINGS INTERESTING.
- BUT SHOULDN'T WE
CONCENTRATE ON THE CEREMONY?
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THE COUNCIL
CATCHES ON TO OUR PLANS.
- NOW VIDALDUS, HOW MANY
TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU
NOT TO WORRY
ABOUT THEM?
- I VOTE YES.
- LEIJI, NOT YOU TOO?
- THERE'S NO OTHER CHOICE.
- TWO MORE VOTES ARE NEEDED.
PLEASE, TRUST ME ON THIS.
- THE MAGIC COUNCIL ONLY WISHES
THEY HAD THE POWER TO STOP ME.
- Natsu: HEY BLOCKHEAD.
- Lucy: GEEZ. WOULD
YOU KEEP IT DOWN?
- Gary: I DON'T SEE THE POINT
IN SNEAKING AROUND ANYMORE.
NOT AFTER ALL THAT RUCKUS
THAT WENT ON DOWNSTAIRS.
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU GUYS EATING?
- I SUGGEST YOU JOIN THEM
BEFORE THERE'S NOTHING LEFT.
- NO THANKS.
- Juvia: THE DOOR
THAT WELCOMED US IN
WAS CONTROLLED BY A MAGIC USER.
- Lucy: THEN THEY ARE WELL
AWARE OF OUR PRESENCE.
WHY WOULD THEY LET US IN?
- Gary: YOU THINK THEY'RE
TRYING TO PROVOKE US?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- NOT TO BE RUDE
BUT YOUR BIKINI
LEAVES LITTLE TO
THE IMAGINATION.
- SHOULD I CHANGE?
- YES. I'LL HELP YOU.
- WAIT? YOU MEAN, RIGHT HERE?
- HOLY...
- PLEASE STOP LOOKING
AT HER, GRAY.
- I BROUGHT THIS OVER FOR YOU
FROM THE CELESTIAL WORLD.
- SO BOYS, DO I LOOK SUPER
CUTE IN THIS OUTFIT OR WHAT?
- OH, YEAH. YOU LOOK GREAT.
- DON'T COMPLIMENT HER.
- HE LOVES HER.
- DON'T YOU START
DOING THAT, TOO.
- AND JUST WHEN WERE YOU
HANGING OUT WITH HAPPY, BIRDO?
- ( sneezes )
- I THINK I'M GOING TO GO
CRAZY IF I HAVE TO STAY
IN THIS PLACE MUCH LONGER.
- I WISH YOU LUCK, PRINCESS.
- THANKS FOR THE HELP, VIRGO.
OH, DID YOU GUYS WANT ME
TO ASK HER TO BRING YOU
A DRY CHANGE OF CLOTHES, TOO?
- NAH, THIS DOES
THE TRICK JUST FINE.
- HE'S NOT A DRYER, YOU KNOW.
- THE INTRUDERS.
- WE FOUND THEM.
- ERZA.
- THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE OKAY.
- WOW. SHE'S SO COOL.
- IT'S YOU. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING INSIDE THE TOWER?
- LOOKING FOR YOU.
- WE HAVEN'T MET,
MY NAME IS JUVIA AND...
- GO HOME. THIS PLACE
IS FAR TOO DANGEROUS.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SCARE ME INTO LEAVING.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
TILL THAT BLOCKHEAD
GETS A GOOD TASTE OF MY FIST.
I'M GOING TO MAKE HIM PAY
FOR SHOOTIN' ME IN THE MOUTH.
- YOU HAVE TO GO.
- BUT WHY?
- YOUR FRIENDS KIDNAPPED HAPPY.
I CAN'T LEAVE HERE WITHOUT HIM.
- THEY GOT HIM TOO?
IT MUST HAVE BEEN MILLIANNA.
- WHERE CAN I FIND HIM?
- IN THE OCEAN?
- Erza: I'M NOT SURE.
- THIS MEANS WAR.
- WHO'RE YOU DECLARING
WAR AGAINST?
- THE JERKS THAT KIDNAPPED
MY LITTLE BUDDY.
- WAIT. NATSU.
- WHAT A MORON.
- POOR NATSU.
- LET'S GO AND HELP HIM.
- NO.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT HAPPY.
MILLIANNA IS A CAT LOVER,
SHE'D NEVER DO ANYTHING
TO HURT HIM.
I PROMISE I'LL BRING THEM BOTH
BACK TO THE GUILD WITH ME
BUT YOU THREE NEED
TO LEAVE IMMEDIATELY.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
WE CAN HELP YOU.
- I DON'T WANT YOUR HELP.
THIS IS MY PROBLEM,
IT DOESN'T INVOLVE YOU.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY
THAT? YOU SAW NATSU.
I'D SAY WE'RE PLENTY INVOLVED.
- ERZA, WHAT'S UP
WITH THIS TOWER?
AND WHO IS THIS JELLAL GUY?
I CAN UNDERSTAND IF YOU
DON'T WANT TO TELL US.
YOU SAID THE CREEPS
WHO KIDNAPPED YOU
USED TO BE FRIENDS
OF YOURS, RIGHT?
WELL, WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS NOW
AND WE'RE HERE TO HELP YOU.
AND NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
WE'RE ALWAYS GOING
TO HAVE YOUR BACK.
- YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
- LEAVE.
- COME ON.
- YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT 'CAUSE
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU AT ALL.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE WOMAN
WHO'D TELL US TO SHUT UP
AND COME ALONG WHETHER
WE WANTED TO OR NOT?
WE WANNA STAY HERE
AND HELP YOU OUT.
MASTER TAUGHT US THAT EVEN
THE STRONGEST WARRIORS
NEED A LITTLE BACKUP
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
- I'M SORRY. BUT YOU
CAN'T HELP ME NOW,
THE ODDS ARE
STACKED AGAINST ME.
WIN OR LOSE THIS BATTLE,
I'M STARING DEATH IN THE FACE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- THERE'S NO POINT IN FIGHTING
WHAT'S INEVITABLE. I CAN'T.
BUT WHAT I CAN DO
IS SHARE MY STORY
WITH YOU WHILE I'M STILL HERE.
THIS BUILDING IS THE
TOWER OF HEAVEN.
IT'S ALSO CALLED THE R-SYSTEM.
OVER A DECADE AGO,
A CULT DEDICATED TO BLACK
MAGIC BEGAN IT'S CONSTRUCTION.
IT WOULD BE USED TO
CAST A FORBIDDEN SPELL
THAT BRINGS THE
DEAD BACK TO LIFE.
THE SPELL REQUIRED
MULTIPLE HUMAN SACRIFICES
SO THE CULT ABDUCTED CITIZENS
OF THE SURROUNDING AREAS
AND FORCED THEM TO BUILD
THE TOWER AS THEIR SLAVES.
THE ONLY REASON I
KNOW THIS IS BECAUSE
I WAS ONE OF
THOSE PEOPLE.
- ( all gasp )
- ANYONE WHO DARED TO
RESIST THE CULT
OR TRIED TO ESCAPE THE TOWER
WOULD MYSTERIOUSLY DISAPPEAR.
WE NEVER HAD ANY PEACE OF MIND.
WE LIVED IN CONSTANT FEAR.
BUT WE BONDED AND MADE FRIENDS
WE COULD TRUST DESPITE THAT,
EVEN THOUGH WE KNEW WE
WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER LONG.
ONE OF MY FRIENDS IN THE TOWER
WAS A BOY NAMED JELLAL.
- ( fighting noises )
- ERZA. HOLD ON.
DON'T WORRY, I'LL
GET YOU OUT OF HERE.
YOUR EYE.
THEY'VE GONE TOO FAR. WHAT
DID SHE DO TO DESERVE THIS?
WHAT DID ANY OF US DO?
( cries ) NO.
- JELLAL.
- THAT'S RIGHT. IT'S ME. YOU'LL
BE SAFE NOW. I'M HERE WITH YOU.
- HOW'LL WE GET OUT?
- WELL, THERE'S NO
TURNING BACK NOW.
WE ARE GOING TO FIGHT.
- WE HAVE TO FIGHT.
- OH, NO. MAGIC SOLDIERS.
- Sho: I HOPE SISTER'S GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
GRANDPA ROB, YOU CAME BACK
FROM PUNISHMENT ALIVE.
YOU THINK SHE'LL BE OKAY?
- I'M SURE SHE'S
GOING TO BE FINE.
THEY CAN TORTURE
HER ALL DAY AND NIGHT
BUT THEY'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO TAKE HER SOUL AWAY FROM HER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- Guard: GET IN.
- Sho: SISTER.
- Simon: ERZA. WAIT A MINUTE,
WHERE'S JELLAL?
- Grandpa Rob: DON'T UPSET
HER ANY MORE.
WE SHOULD JUST BE HAPPY
SHE'S COME BACK TO US ALIVE.
- BUT GRANDPA...
- I CAN ONLY ASSUME
THEY'VE CHOSEN
TO KEEP HIM IN HER PLACE.
- ( sobs )
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
- QUIT YOUR CRYING, KID.
- CALM DOWN, SHO.
THERE'S NO NEED TO CRY.
EVERYTHING'S GOING
TO WORK OUT JUST FINE.
- Guard: SHUT IT,
YOU LITTLE BRAT.
- Sho: LEAVE ME ALONE.
- Jellal: WE'RE GOING TO FIGHT.
- Simon: WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
- Guard: WHAT THE...
- NO WAY.
- COULD IT BE?
- MUTINY.
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- FIND A WEAPON.
WE CAN'T ESCAPE AND THEY'RE
NOT GOING TO SET US FREE.
SO IF WE WANT OUT OF
HERE, WE HAVE TO FIGHT.
FOR OUR LIVES, FOR OUR FREEDOM.
- ( cheering )
SO WE TOOK A STAND
FOR OUR FREEDOM.
WE HOPED TO SAVE
OUR DEAR FRIEND JELLAL.
HE WAS LIKE THE LEADER
OF OUR GROUP BACK THEN.
HE HAD A STRONG SENSE
OF JUSTICE THAT I TRULY ADMIRED.
HOWEVER...
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO HIM.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF HE BECAME
AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT PERSON.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY I COULD
DESCRIBE JELLAL'S NEW PERSONA,
PURE, UNADULTERATED EVIL.
- HEY NATSU, I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'VE HEARD A REALLY WEIRD
SOUND THE LAST FEW NIGHTS.
- NOTHING OUT OF THE ORDINARY.
WHAT'S IT SOUND LIKE?
- IT'S CREEPY. IT SOUNDS
LIKE A GIRL CRYING,
AND I HEAR IT EVERY NIGHT
BEFORE I GO TO BED.
- REALLY? MAN, THAT
SOUNDS TOTALLY COOL.
- WELL, I DON'T THINK IT'S COOL
'CAUSE I CAN'T SLEEP.
- Natsu and Happy:
NEXT TIME, VOICE OF DARKNESS.
- Natsu: SO DOES THIS GHOST
OF YOURS SAY ANYTHING
IN PARTICULAR?
- Happy: "THE RENT.
MUST PAY THE RENT."
- Natsu: UH, I'M PRETTY
SURE THAT'S JUST LUCY.