[DORANBOLT] Man...
I am going on a bender when
we're done with all this.
Speaking of,
are you getting any closer?
[LAHAR] I think I'm finally
starting to connect the dots.
[LAHAR] I can't thank you
enough, Doranb--
[LAHAR] Mest.
♪
[LAHAR] The Neo-Oración
Seis has been destroying
churches all over Fiore.
The attacks seemed random...
...but I've found evidence
that those churches
were secretly sheltering people.
[DORANBOLT] What's
so special about 'em...?
Was there any record of them
in Zentopia's documents?
[LAHAR] They were assumed
to be corpses at first...
However...
[DORANBOLT]
They're still kickin' huh?.
I sense a bit of
life from them, yes.
It's similar
to a Freezing Seal...
Almost as if...
No, that's not important now.
[LAHAR] I believe
there may be some kind
of cabal operating
within Zentopia.
All signs point to something
big about to go down...
...and it's centered
around them.
[DORANBOLT] Sounds like
we need to figure out who
they are before they wind
up as stiff as their buddies.
What is it, Nico?
Did you hear something?
[Nico grunts]
[HAPPY] Anti-Link!
Oh, my...
Hello, boys.
[GRAY] She's with the
Neo-Oración Seis!
[FRIED] Angel,
if I'm not mistaken.
[DAN] What...
...a...
...babe!
[DAN] You're the cherubic
beauty of my dreams!
[ANGEL] That's not really
a compliment, y'know.
[FRIED] Who is that...?
One of her allies?
[GRAY] Are you kidding?!
[ANGEL] Are you kidding?!
[DAN] Dan Straight of the Legion
Platoon, at your service...!
Loopy-Pie is old news now...
I've dedicated my
heart to this angel!
I'll have you know...
My loyalty lies with Laxus.
Why are you competing
with each other?!
[GRAY] Alright lady...
...what did you do
with the Infinity Clock?!
[ANGEL] What
an idiotic question.
Cost is forty...
Come forth from the light...
[ANGEL] In my name,
embrace thy holy might!
Angel Magic...
Be on guard.
[DAN] She's so
heavenly...! I'm on fire!
But that darkness
in her eyes bothers me...
My spear'll set her straight.
[ANGEL] O angel of the sunlight,
Shamsiel, I summon thee.
[SHAMSIEL] Hiiii...!
What's up, fellas?
[GRAY] What the hell is that?
[DAN] I don't know,
but he's chubby and cute!
I found some
playmates for you.
[SHAMSIEL] Oh boy!
Let's play catch...!
Who wants to go first?
[DAN] I'll play with you!
I'm great at catch!
That hurt!
[GRAY] You're not even
supposed to be here anyway!
Dark Écriture...
Pain!
Ice Make: Saucer!
[SHAMSIEL] Cut it out...!
That tickles!
[SHAMSIEL] An angel's light
is like a thousand suns...
See for yourself!
May your own
voice destroy you.
[ERZA] Stay down...!
I'll handle this!
[COBRA] Do you know
where Cubellios is?
Don't try to hide
anything from me, Titania.
[COBRA] I see...
You really don't know.
[MAX] So, what,
you're just gonna
answer your own questions?!
[ERZA] His magic allows
him to hear our thoughts.
You better not be sifting
through anything private!
[COBRA] If you can't help
me, I don't need you.
[ERZA] Stay down...!
I'll handle this!
[MAX] What was that?!
[EVERGREEN] More than
just a "listening" spell!
He absorbed the sound
of my voice and amplified it...
Then used it to attack...
Very clever.
[COBRA] I can hear it...
You plan to use
the elasticity of
your clothing to
weaken my attack...
...and land a
strike of your own.
Close...
but no cigar.
I hear everything...
even your movements.
[COBRA] You never
cease to impress...
You're more dexterous
than ever before...
No wonder you defeated
Azuma of Grimoire Heart.
[ERZA THINKS] Natsu beat him by
attacking without thinking,
and then deafened
him with a roar.
[COBRA] You don't honestly think
I'm that stupid, do you...?
I'm not gonna fall
for the same trick twice.
[ERZA] We'll see!
Seven years ago...
I lost Cubellios...
And Fairy Tail...
took her away from me!
[MAX] Erza!
[EVERGREEN] Erza!
[COBRA] Give her back...
Return Cubellios to me now!
[ERZA] Who is that?!
[KATJA] There's nothing
to worry about...
It's probably just the
servant staff coming
back from their supply run.
[door opens]
Hello?
Afternoon.
[KATJA] Who're you?
[LAHAR] A spirit!
You're a Celestial wizard?
[DORANBOLT] Wendy?!
[KATJA] Run!
Listen, please!
Let go of me!
[LAHAR] Calm down!
My name's Lahar... Chief
Marshal of the Council's...
Custody Enforcement unit.
I'm conducting
an investigation.
Into what, exactly?
[Nico grunts questioningly]
[DORANBOLT] I bet Wendy would
look a lot like this girl...
if she were still alive...
If I hadn't abandoned her.
[WENDY] Stay strong...!
Come on, Bixlow, I know
you can pull through this.
Forget about me...
Run while you still can!
[ERIGOR] Listen to him...
...give up and run away.
Unless you'd like
to join him in suffering.
[Wendy screams]
[ERIGOR] Do you see how
futile your fight is now...?
Nobody stands a chance
against the raw power of nature.
[ERIGOR] If you abandon
him, you might
have a chance of
escaping with your life...
Why go to him instead?
[WENDY] Because...
As long as I'm breathing,
I'll never abandon a friend!
What a fool.
[BIXLOW] Dammit, kid...!
Quit playin' hero and
get out of here already!
I know it ain't fair,
but sometimes you
gotta leave your friends behind!
[WENDY] No, you're wrong...!
I'm not moving from this spot,
so shut up and let me save you!
[ERIGOR] Friends?
What is this?!
[ERIGOR] Who was that?
What did you do to me?!
[BIXLOW] I dunno
what just happened...
But you got to him.
[KATJA] Now Open,
Gate of the Chisel...
Caelum!
[KATJA] Please...
Keep watch over us.
[DORANBOLT THINKS] She can
open two gates at once?
Um... You keep
staring at me.
I know celestial wizards
are kind of rare...
Have you...
...met any of us before?
No, nothing like that...
I don't mean to be creepy...
It's just that you look...
...like somebody that
I used to know.
Oh really, I do?
I know they're flat,
so don't stare!
I didn't even say anything!
[LAHAR] Would you
stop playing around?
[DORANBOLT]
Sorry, I deserved that.
No... I'm the one
who should
apologize to you.
So... who is this girl
that resembles me?
Unfortunately, she passed away
about seven years ago...
But that's...
because I failed her.
[KATJA] You know...
In a strange way...
I envy her.
I mean...
She's been gone awhile...
...but she's able
to live on in the
thoughts of those who knew her.
I'd love to have
someone like that.
But no...
...even after a hundred
years, I'll have no one.
[KATJA] It may sound odd...
...but I gave up
hope a long time ago.
[KATJA] I lost most of
my friends in the attacks...
I'm afraid it's only a matter
of time before I join them.
You've given up on...
...what?
On living...
...in the here and now.
I see.
[KATJA] I'm resigned
to my fate...
So I thought I'd
take in as much of
this era's scenery as I can...
...while I'm here.
But we can protect you...
Katja, I...
Don't listen to me.
[LAHAR] Excuse me...
May I ask...
...are you being sheltered by
the church for some reason?
[KATJA] Yes...
Who are you...?
And who were your friends?
We can help!
Caelum, no!
We're not alone here!
Hey look out!
He's behind you!
I found you.
[DORANBOLT]
Don't worry, I've got ya!
[LAHAR] Be careful, Mest...!
He's dangerous!
Yeah, He's with
the Neo-Oración Seis...
Racer!
[RACER] Destroy...
...vessel...
[CARDINAL 143A]
Time is a luxury we don't have.
[CARDINAL 143B] Word of
the archbishop's madness
has begun to
spread to the outside.
[CARDINAL 143C] We should
select a new archbishop
and continue with
the Founding Festival!
[LAPOINTE]
Everyone calm down...!
Selecting a new Archbishop is
absolutely out of the question,
especially now that the
Infinity Clock is lost to us...
The archbishop is
the sole pillar
of order to our followers...
If we replace him, confusion
and chaos would run rampant!
[CARDINAL 143D]
But, your Eminence...
[CARDINAL 143E]
Is that really wise?
[LAPOINTE]
Pathetic, lowly insects...
Even if they did replace
their precious leader
it would do them no good.
[LAPOINTE] The end is
finally within our grasp.
[RACER] Destroy...
...the vessel...
Destroy!
[RACER] You're a very quick one.
I will have fun destroying you.
Lahar, take Katja and run!
I'll keep her safe.
But what about you?
Just get out of here, alright?!
Are you sure...
He can take care
of himself...
There's no need
for you to worry.
[LAHAR] He may not look it,
but he's a skilled wizard...
Believe me.
[LAHAR] If there's anyone who
can handle this guy, it's Mest.
Thank you...
Please, be careful.
You know, I've abandoned
a lot of things...
But losing my humanity is
a line I'd never cross.
[RACER] Destroy!
Okay, monster...
Let's see which
one of us is faster!
[DORANBOLT] I get it...
You're pretty quick...
But I'm just warming up!
[DORANBOLT] Direct Line!
This guy is so fast it's hard
to see what he's doing...
[DORANBOLT] But from
what I can tell, it looks like
he's moving in simple,
straight lines...
My Direct Line
isn't as restrictive,
so all I gotta do
is circle around him.
I can see your movements...
...fool.
[DORANBOLT] Damn...
I spent way too much
time getting hammered.
This is rough...
[RACER] What's wrong...?
Am I too fast?.
Sorry about that.
This is nothing...
My warm up...
Time for round two.
[ERIGOR] Make it stop!
[ERIGOR] Get out of my head!
I don't want any memories!
[BIXLOW] Looks like this
freak's mind is turnin' on him.
[WENDY] Huh?
Stay away, Kageyama...!
I can't hear myself think!
[BIXLOW] His memories
are trying to come to the
surface but something
else is pushing 'em back.
[BIXLOW] Whatever
you did to remind him is
tearing him apart
from the inside out.
I wanna help him.
If my Healing magic started
this, maybe I can use it to
stop whatever's
blocking his mind.
You really wanna help the
guy who's trying to kill us?!
I have to!
[ERIGOR] You...!
Die!
Sky Dragon Healing...
Roar!
There'll be nothing left
when I'm through with you!
[WENDY] Remember!
[BIXLOW] Geez,
this kid is pushy!
[ERIGOR (YOUNG)] Hey!
Do you have any idea how
pathetic you look right now...?
I find it hard to
believe I'd give up
so much just for power.
[ERIGOR] I know you...
You're me.
Something seriously nasty
just popped out of his soul.
He's in pain...
'cause of me...
All I wanted was
to heal his mind...
...but I ended up
hurting him instead.
[BIXLOW]
Hey may look rough...
But he'll be just fine...
Whatever was clouding
his mind is gone now.
[BIXLOW]
You done good, Wendy.
[LAHAR]
Could you explain it to me?
[KATJA] Yes...
The attacks on the churches
are just a side-effect...
The true goal of
the Neo-Oración Seis
is to perform Anti-Link rites.
What's an "Anti-Link"?
Since Zentopia
was founded,
there's been an
underground society...
It's managed to
remain hidden from the
powers that be since
its inception.
[KATJA] They've worked
to keep the Celestial wizards
of Neville safe and
sheltered all this time.
Neville...?
I'd heard he was
a Celestial wizard...
...but it has never
been confirmed.
He was many things...
Including a great teacher
who had many pupils.
We're their descendants...
Biological links to his work.
[LAHAR] What do you mean?
[KATJA] It's our job
to protect his legacy...
...for as long
as we're still living.
[KATJA]
These crests symbolize that...
Our duty... as well
as our greatest curse.
I'm deeply sorry
for your burden...
I can't even fathom it...
But your friends...
...they are neither
alive nor dead...
What happened to them?
[KATJA] Well...
you see...
Run for it...
Wendy...
[LAHAR] No!
Once I perform the
Amplitude Limiter Anti-Link...
...your pain will end.
[KATJA THINKS] This is it...
I knew this day would come.
What just
happened here?
Beats me... But I
could sure use a drink...
Are you okay?
[DORANBOLT] Oh, no!
[DORANBOLT]
But she wasn't hit...
Was she?!
[DORANBOLT] Katja...!
C'mon, stay with me!
[Racer laughs]
The Anti-Link
has been completed.
[thunder]
[MIDNIGHT] At last we meet...
Will Neville.
You've picked a rather dreary
place to rest for eternity...
Can't say I envy you.
Guess what...?
I've taken care of
your pupils for you...
And I didn't hear
a single 'thank you.'
Don't worry...
I'll take care of
your legacy as well...
Every bit of it...
After all, nightmares
are my specialty.
[DORANBOLT]
Good, you're awake...
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine...
But what about you?
You shouldn't
worry about me...
But can you tell us what
the hell just happened?
The Anti-Link
must've been activated...
I don't feel the
biological link anymore.
But it seems my curse
didn't take effect.
[LAHAR] Are you sure?
Because it looks as though
you've lost your magic power.
[KATJA] Nico...
Thanks for everything
you've done...
I'll never forget you
or the others, I swear.
[Nico moans]
Yeah, you're right...
And, it won't be in
a hundred years...!
I'm sure...
...we'll meet again soon.
So you can understand
what its saying?
Kind of...
I can only catch a little
bit here and there, but...
I'm pretty sure he's saying
"Thanks for helping."
[KATJA] He also says,
"Get your paw off her."
[DORANBOLT] My bad!
I assume this means you're
no longer a Celestial wizard.
[DORANBOLT] I'm sorry...
When it came down to it...
I simply wasn't
able to protect you.
[KATJA] No, you're wrong...
You did protect me...
...from a horrific curse.
If you hadn't been here
I'd be as good as dead now...
So, thank you...
You saved my life.
You're my hero.
[DORANBOLT] Thanks...
But... I'm not.
Do you it
see now, Mest...?
If you let the past
hold you back...
...you'll miss out on more
chances to change the future...
Like today.
[DORANBOLT]
Cut the philosophical crap.
And by the way...
Mest is gone...
My name is Doranbolt.
[LAHAR THINKS] Finally...
...you've broken
free of your past...
Now you will truly have
the chance to thrive.
This is the beginning of
a new day for you, old friend.
[HAPPY] I just can't
seem to shake it...
I've got a weird feelin'
that something is "off,"
just like Samuel said...
I don't like it.
I'm--so--pissed!
Why's it so hard to land a punch
on a talking slot machine?!
Just fight us head-on,
ya coward!
I've got a bad feeling...
It's almost like Cana's
fortunetelling backfired on us.
Well I've got some
'front-fire'...
...and I can't wait to use it!
Natsu, hold on a minute!
[HAPPY] Lucy's dad left her
a hand of the Infinity Clock...
Then Zentopia went after it.
[HAPPY] In the end...
Fairy Tail and the
Legion Platoon were
completely fooled by
the Neo-Oración Seis.
We fell right into their trap.
[LUCY] Natsu!
[NATSU]
Look, I'm still standing!
You gambled and
lost, ya freak show...!
And now Fairy Tail
is here to collect!
[LUCY] Yeah...!
Whether Cana was right or not,
we still gotta take
this joker down!
Now you're talkin'!
[HAPPY] I can't
shake the feeling that
we're overlooking
somethin' really important...
But what could it be?
[HAPPY] Natsu...
I hope you're okay...
[GILDARTS] That's it.
I think we've hit
the end of the line.
[LAKI] Wait Gildarts...
Check it out!
[GILDARTS] Is that a girl?
[LAKI] It looks like...
she's still alive.
[GILDARTS] Who is she...?
And why is she tucked
away in this musty old cave?
[LAKI] Well, according to
this chart, she underwent
heavy treatment here after a big
accident several years ago.
And what's strange,
is that even if she recovers,
that lacrima will keep her
in a comatose state.
Someone wanted
sleeping beauty to stay
asleep for a real long time.
Do you have any
clue who she might be?
It says here...
That she's Michelle Lobster...
...and I'll bet you this
one is the real deal.
Hold up...
This girl is Michelle?
[LAKI] Apparently so...
[LAKI] The sole
daughter and surviving
member of the Lobster family...
Everyone else died in an
accident on their plantation.
Wait...
I'm confused...
If she's here...
Then who's the girl that's
been hangin' around Lucy?!
♪
[NATSU] Whoa, what's
with that horrible ringing?!
Is it comin' from the sky?!
[HAPPY]
It must be the lunch bell!
Perfect timing too,
I was getting' hungry.
Bring on the noms!
[NATSU] Already?
In that case, let's stuff our
faces and put it on Lucy's tab!
[HAPPY] Aye, sir...!
Wait, look out!
Giant flying fish
at twelve o'clock!
[NATSU] Cool!
How about we just
eat that instead?!
[HAPPY AND NATSU]]
Next time: Despair Unleashed!
[HAPPY] Are you sure it's
even edible, Natsu?
[NATSU] Most things are,
if you put your mind to it.
[HAPPY] Really?
Then you can eat some rocks.
This fish is all mine.