[LUCY] The world had
never seen a thief of his kind.
Like a grotesque shadow,
he moved unbridled
through the darkness.
The sight of his bizarre visage
caused even the bravest
of men to falter.
And no matter the odds,
he always got his prize.
[LUCY as MONKEY MAN A]
Give up, jewel thief!
You can't take us
all out at once!
[LUCY as MONKEY MAN B] Come on!
Give me a reason to shoot you!
[evil laugh]
[LUCY as INVISIBLE MAN]
Pathetic.
Did you numbskulls honestly
think you would be able
to catch a brilliant
thief like me?
[LUCY as FEMALE A]
It's a ghost!
[LUCY as FEMALE B]
No, it's a demon!
[LUCY as INVISIBLE MAN]
Now, fools, tremble in terror
as you gaze upon the
true form of your enemy!
[LUCY] What can the
hearts of men do
against such a wretched
and desolate foe?
What mettle can
withstand his horror?
The poor souls
that dared to stand up
to him that night found
only fear and futility.
Their courage vanished
as quickly as their quarry
into the endless night.
[evil laugh]
Done.
[NATSU] So that's the kind
of stuff Lucy writes, huh?
[LUCY] Hey, Put those down!
Who gave you
permission to read that!
You.
I think.
So is this
"Invisible Man" guy
a new character
you're working on?
Yep.
Sure is!
I'm taking a stab at
a new genre so I can
stretch my writing
legs a bit, y'know?
I mean, everyone's
imagined what it would be like
to be invisible at least
once in their life, right?
So I thought it would
make an awesome premise
for a horror novel!
Pathetic!
Did you numbskulls honestly
think you would ever be able
to catch a brilliant
kitty cat like me?
Hey!
Now fools,
tremble in terror as
you gaze upon the true form
of your enemy!
You're killing my
self-esteem here!
♪
[LUCY] Is there a reason
you're invading my privacy?
If you're just here to
play, then there's the door.
We'd like your
help on a big job.
You're gonna end up broke if
you don't get some work in soon.
Thanks, but I'm busy right now.
You're big boys, you can handle
a job without me this once.
Sorry, no dice.
The three of us are
a team, remember?
Aye!
[NATSU] We can't
go without you.
It would be the same!
How sweet.
And we haven't
eaten all day!
Got any scraps
we could chow on?
[LUCY] Go eat out of
the trash, you bums!
[HAPPY] The Terror
of Invisible Lucy!
Those jerks.
Thanks to them I've got
major writer's block.
I bet a nice hot bath
will make that disappear.
A magic potion?
Oh yeah, I forgot
I brewed one of my own before
we left for Tenrou Island.
I didn't get the chance
to try it but it's supposed
to leave your skin super clear!
I think I found
my bath mate for today!
[LUCY] I'm kinda jealous
of The Invisible Man.
I think it'd be
really cool to have
the power of invisibility.
Think of all
the pranks I could pull!
And it would be super
useful on jobs, too!
That'd be awesome!
[LUCY] That was nice.
but I probably look
like a raisin now.
[LUCY] What the heck?
No way!
Did I really turn invisible!
Hold on.
The potion has been
fermenting for seven years!
This is crazy!
Has it been
sitting out for so long
that its effects have changed?!
[LUCY] I can't stay like this!
Maybe someone at the
guild can help me out.
Oh. Oh no.
If I go outside like this,
there's a good chance
I'll cause a panic!
[LANDLADY] Huh?
That's strange.
Must have just been the wind.
[LUCY] Okay, no one here can
see me, so I need to make sure
I don't bump into them.
No need to worry.
I'll stick to the side.
Oh wow, I just rushed
out here without thinking.
I actually forgot that I'm
around town in my birthday suit
right now.
If the effects of the potion
suddenly start
wearing off, then--
[LUCY] I'd have to move away.
But that's not gonna
stop me from enjoying it
while it lasts!
[LUCY] Okay world, gaze
in awe at my see-through
miracle of a bod!
Is it hot out, or is it me?
How about this pose?
You like that don't ya?
I am Lucy, hear me roar!
[LUCY] Wow.
Maybe all the exhibitionists
are on to something here.
[LUCY] Hey.
Knock it off!
Shoo!
There's nothing there, big guy.
Your nose must be
losin' its touch.
Whose voice was that?
[LUCY] That was a close one.
I need to get to
the guild hall A-S-A-P!
Whoa, did we just
slam into thin air?
Seems like it.
[BOY A] Hold on!
I can feel something!
[GIRL A] It keeps
moving around, too!
[BOY B] It's
shaped like a person!
Not good.
Stop!
You're gonna
make me pee myself!
[LUCY] Get off of me,
you little monsters!
It's trying to escape!
[KIDS]
We're gonna get you!
A vengeful spirit!
Catch it!
[LUCY] Persistent little brats!
This is not a game!
Awesome!
I'll hide over there.
[KIDS] Get back here!
I'm glad they're gone.
Sweet!
Now to get me back to normal!
She has got you
so whipped.
So,
does Lucy kick the two of
you guys out all the time?
Yeah.
And we were offering her
work; you would think
she'd at least say 'thank you'.
You deserved
a swift kick in the pants!
From what I hear, you barge
into her apartment and treat it
like some cheap hotel!
If it had been me, I would
have clawed your eyes out.
Carla has a point, Natsu.
Lucy is your teammate.
You should treat her
with more respect.
If you're
feeling hungry.
You know that you're always
welcome to come here and eat
from the bar instead.
Wow.
Are you sure you really
wanna make him that offer?
She kicked him out
cause he's a pig, ya know?
Well, Lucy could try
being a little nicer
to everybody
once in a while.
That's probably the reason
all of the single guys
in town call her
the "Blonde beast."
They hit the
nail on the head!
Yeah, she's about
as likely to start dating
as Droy is to go vegetarian.
You can take the rich
girl out of the mansion
but not the other
way around!
I have no idea
what that means,
but it sounded manly,
so I'll go along with it.
[DROY] If you ask me, Lucy could
stand to learn a thing or two
about being a lady from Levy.
Yeah, she's cute
and delicate, like a flower.
It's nice of you to say,
but I don't know if 'delicate'
is even in Lucy's vocabulary.
[LUCY] Let's see how much they
laugh when I have a little fun
at their expense!
Hey!
You got a problem, wise guy?
Wha-?
You're the one
with the problem!
Don't play dumb.
Wasting booze is bad enough,
but bathing me in it is suicide!
I think you've had
one too many, ol' pal.
Fine, if it wasn't you
then who did it?
Beats me!
That's my ear,
not a potato chip!
Eat my fist!
Sorry, but I'm not
into eating fatty meat!
Been awhile since
we've had a pointless brawl!
Okay, I must have
missed something.
Dad spilt his drink
and now he's throwing
a temper tantrum.
You'd think they'd learn
to take the rough stuff outside.
It was almost finished.
Now I have to start all over!
[NATSU] What the
heck was that for!
Are you lookin' for
a fight, punk?
My breakfast
will be avenged!
[GRAY] What're
you talkin' about?
I didn't touch
your nasty food!
You hit me!
Then get out of
the way of our fight, man!
Why do you even
stand here?
Everyone knows you'll
never take a job!
I may not have a job,
but I can sure as hell
can drop some pain
on you meatheads!
What are they fighting
each other for!
Calm down, everyone!
Let's talk this out!
This is nothing new.
Just let them have at it.
But if they keep this
up there won't be
a guild hall
to fight in.
Then we'll make them
rebuild it later today.
We must set an example and
not get involved their antics.
And they wonder why
the guild has fallen so low.
Did the lessons of the past
seven years just pass them by?
Very well then.
I guess I'll
just have to teach you!
What was that about
'setting an example'?
She always finds a reason
to join in the fun.
I really should come
to expect this kind of
behavior from them.
[LUCY] Okay.
I may have gone
a little overboard.
[LUCY yells]
I thought I heard Lucy.
That's weird.
And I can smell her!
It really is you!
[LUCY screams]
[LUCY] Watch where
you're touching, perv!
Is that Lucy?
I didn't know
she was here.
I definitely
heard her though.
Yet we can't see her.
Maybe she's
trapped behind the wall!
Now the cat's
outta the bag.
[MAX] Does anybody else
find this really weird?
[GRAY] To be honest,
I'm too confused to know
what I'm thinkin.
[LUCY] Hey,
could you guys please
not stare at me like that?
It's embarrassing!
[ALL] Creepy!
[LUCY] Thanks a lot!
I've never seen a
potion do this before.
It's good you're wearing
clothes now so we can see you.
but still.
Do you know how
to change back?
[LUCY] Well.
actually, I was kind of
hoping someone here
could help me with that.
If you ask me, you
shouldn't worry
about changing back.
You should go on some
jobs first; you're like
the perfect ninja
assassin now!
[LUCY] I'm not
a freakin' hit man!
There has to be
a way to fix this!
Does anyone know a remedy?
I'll try anything!
Wish I could
help you, but.
Don't worry; I know
just what to do!
[LUCY] Really!
If I burn all the potion
stuff off you should go back
to normal, right?
[LUCY] What makes you
think that would even work!
Knowing Natsu, I'd say
that's his 'go-to remedy'
for just about every
problem he faces.
Well it's the only idea
we've got at the moment.
So let's give it a shot.
It's time to grit your
teeth and go for broke,
like a real man would!
That's it.
I'm dead.
Okay, I'm giving
it my all, Lucy.
One good flame
deserves another!
[LUCY] H-Hold on!
On second thought,
I'll just stay invisible!
[NATSU and ROMEO] Ready...
...go!
[LUCY screams]
Huh.
Guess ya need more fire.
[LUCY] No, I do not!
Come on Lu,
don't be sad.
We'll have you
fixed up in no time.
Oui.
Don't worry, my dear, I live
for situations like this!
You do?
[LUCY] I'll try anything
as long as it's not fire!
Leave it to me, Madame.
I'll paint you a face that will
be considered a masterpiece!
Well,
it's definitely...
a unique face.
Actually, I think
you look prettier
than you did before!
[LUCY] Uh, no.
I'll pass.
I've always wanted
to try cubism!
Hey I'm not
a canvas!
Why don't you let a true
master take a crack at it?
That's my brush!
All done!
Whatcha think?
This is worse
than the last one!
Yeah, you need to bring
her eyes in closer,
and her nostrils
are way too tiny.
And this eyebrow
isn't bushy enough.
'Kay...
what next?
[LUCY] You're not helping!
First.
We should start by
fixing her eye brows.
You wanna darken around her
eyes so they'll really pop.
kinda like this.
Step aside amateurs; I'll
make her good as new.
You've got no
sense of anatomy.
Luckily, I took art
classes in grade school
for a couple
of days.
Facial hair
is a necessity.
Personally I'm a huge
fan of the Fu Manchu.
Every girl strives to be
the pinnacle of cuteness.
Sparkly eyes really
help with that.
You know, I've
always wanted to
see you with
darker hair.
It'll give you more
of a gothy look!
Personally, I'd like to see
some different hairstyles.
Like a short pixie cut,
or maybe dreadlocks!
I think she's more of
an afro kinda chick.
Well, You can't have an afro
without groovy face paint!
[LUCY] Screw you guys!
I'm not a freakin' toy!
Sup bro'?
Why would
you do this to me!
Too much work.
This should
fix her up.
Maker magic
for the win!
It's even got nose
holes for breathing.
[ALL] Creepy!
[LUCY] You are the
worst friends ever!
[LUCY] Okay,
what is this thing?
We ripped it out of
an old Sorcerer
Weekly centerfold.
You can't see
out of it, but at least
you have your face back.
[LUCY] Well, it's better
than the last option was,
that's for sure.
Oui.
It's much better.
We're back!
So, what did you two
go rushing off for?
To search Lucy's
apartment!
We found the potion bottle.
And I thought you might
want your Celestial Keys.
[LUCY] Oh, yeah!
I didn't think of asking
my Celestial Spirits for help!
I owe you big time!
Thanks a lot, ladies!
But I'm not sure
which one I should summon.
Loki and Aquarius are my
strongest but I doubt they'd
be much help in this situation.
You should bring out the
gremlins that copy people!
[LUCY] You mean
Gemini? What for?
Duh, we're gonna have them
change into you, silly!
Just summon them already!
[LUCY] Okay.
Open, Gate of the Twins!
Gemini!
[LUCY (GEMINI)] Gemini's
coming at ya Lucy style!
[MACAO] Hey.
I can see her again!
[WAKABA] You know
that's not really her.
[HAPPY] Way to go, Gemini!
[HAPPY] Now the magic happens!
[LUCY (GEMINI)]
Hello, my name is Lucy.
Would you like to be best
friends with me forever?
If she does this
the rest of her life,
the problem's solved!
This is perfect!
Nice work, Happy!
[LUCY] This doesn't solve
anything, coal-for-brains!
[GRAY] Man, you really
do look just like her.
Crazy.
[LUCY (GEMINI)] I also copied
her thoughts and abilities.
Cool, huh?
And I can maintain
this form indefinitely.
[MAX] If that's the case,
couldn't we just say
this is the real Lucy?
That'd work for me.
[JET] It'd make all of this a
lot easier, so I'm down for it.
[DROY] Yeah, and this Lucy
is friendlier and far more
lady-like than the old one was.
[LUCY] I'm still here!
We were just joking!
You two sure got
quiet; is everything okay?
Yeah, we're just analyzing
the potion's recipe.
If we figure out
how the magic works.
then we can
create an Enchantment
to reverse its effect.
That was
a piece of cake.
Here ya go.
A complete list
of the components.
Thanks.
Now leave the rest to me!
This Enchantment will
nullify the potion's effect.
So sit perfectly still.
It will be over soon!
[MACAO] So, uh.
Did it work or not?
[WAKABA] Don't look at me.
[LUCY] Are you sure
you wrote it correctly?
I am.
The effects have been dealt
with, but since the potion
had seven years to mature.
It will take just as long
for the Enchantment to work.
[LUCY] Can't you do anything
to speed up the process!
[LEVY] Sorry, Lu.
[Lucy begins to cry]
I don't get it, why
are you laughing?
[LUCY] I'm not!
I'm crying, you
insensitive jerk!
[LUCY] Hey, what's
happening to me?
Why are my clothes
starting to disappear!
No, I was afraid
something like
this would happen.
[ERZA] Like what?
What's going on here!
Time can drastically
change a potion's effects.
And I think this one has
gotten way more powerful.
She's not just
turning invisible.
I'm afraid her very existence
is being removed from history.
The bottle
just vanished!
If her existence
is being nullified,
it makes sense for her personal
belongings to vanish too.
I bet you everything in
her apartment is disappearing
as we speak!
No...
This can't be happening to me.
I don't wanna disappear;
I wanna live!
Look, I'm right here,
plain as day.
You see?
I'm as real as you!
Weird; I totally blanked
on what I was talking about.
Yes.
I suppose it wasn't
very important.
[REEDUS] I could have sworn
I was in the middle of
painting something.
But what?
This sounds weird.
but I feel like
there's someone else
who's supposed
to be here with us.
I'm having a
similar feeling myself.
How odd.
Could we be under the
effects of a malicious spell
or Enchantment?
I dunno.
Guess It's possible.
Are you feeling
anything weird, Natsu?
I'm hungry?
Come on,
I'm right in front of you!
What's the matter?
Can't you hear me?
Oh well, I guess it's
back to the daily grind then.
[REEDUS] Fried,
if you're not busy,
I could really use
a model for more practice.
Yes, of course.
Natsu!
Stop drinking and look at me!
Hey Gray?
Can you hear me?
[LUCY] Erza!
Happy!
Wendy!
Carla!
Please Don't forget me!
Too late.
The damage has been done.
[LUCY] Every one of my friends
has forgotten about me.
Because I never
existed in their world.
I'm like a ghost that
can't even haunt anyone.
I refuse to live this way!
[NATSU] Ahh, much better!
I'm ready to tackle the day!
Happy, go find Lucy
so we can get rocking!
Aye, Sir!
Lucy?
Oh yeah!
Lucy!
[NATSU AND HAPPY] She's our
best friend and teammate!
The one who completes us!
Yes, I remember now!
How could we forget her?
I need to quit drinkin'.
Yeah we love her.
Hey.
I'm back!
Great to see you again!
Welcome back!
I guess that was
kind of a close call.
I wonder if Natsu is
the one who broke the spell.
[MAX] Yeah.
I think you might
be right there.
His mind may have
forgotten her,
but she was still tucked
away in his heart.
No ordinary magic could
trump our guild's bonds!
In your face, potion!
Yes, that's certainly
a fine sentiment.
Everything's back to normal.
Not that you three contributed
to that in the least.
[LUCY] Thanks a lot, Natsu.
What, did you think
losing your existence
would get you
out of work today?
Think again!
Aye!
[LUCY] It turns out being
invisible really wasn't
all that bad in the end.
[LUCY] But the loneliness I
felt when I thought I'd been
forgotten was the worst
feeling in the world.
[LUCY] My guild mates may
not be the most reliable.
But, at the end of the day,
they're a dear and precious
part of my life.
Ya know, I should
probably get rid of this thing.
I'm so glad you're
not dead, Lucy!
[HAPPY] Natsu!
[group talking over one another]
Yep, those
are my friends.
I really wish they'd learn to
get their act together though.
♪
[HAPPY] Have you seen
Elfman around anywhere?
[NATSU] Yeah, he just
stepped out to run
some errands for Mira.
[HAPPY] I wish I had
a little brother, too.
[NATSU] Why?
[HAPPY] Are you kidding?
It'd be awesome!
He'd go shopping for me,
cook for me, give me back rubs,
and I'd always get one more
fish, because I'm the oldest!
[HAPPY] Next time:
Father's Memento!
I'm pretty sure there's not
a little brother in the world
who would do all of that crap.
[HAPPY] Isn't that how
siblings are though?
[NATSU] Is it?
Now I kinda want one!