- Natsu: PREVIOUSLY
ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
- Gray: WE FOUGHT HARD AGAINST
THE ORACION SEIS,
BUT THEY WERE ABLE
TO KIDNAP HAPPY AND WENDY.
- Carla: UNFORTUNATELY ERZA
WAS POISONED IN THE BATTLE
AND WENDY'S
SKY DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC
IS THE ONLY THING
THAT CAN HELP HER.
- Natsu:
SO WE SPLIT UP INTO GROUPS
TO FIND OUT WHERE
THOSE JERKS TOOK THEM,
BUT WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
HANG ON, GUYS.
WE'RE COMING TO GET YOU.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( gasps )
- ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO JELLAL,
A BRILLIANT WIZARD WHO ONCE
INFILTRATED THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
- ( laughing )
- HEY, BRO',
I GOT A GREAT IDEA.
LET'S SHOW THESE GUYS
JUST HOW TERRIFYING
NAKED MUMMY CAN BE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
- THAT'S SOUNDS FUN.
GOOD IDEA,
BUT I'M AFRAID THEY WON'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT HIT 'EM
'CAUSE IT'D
BE OVER SO QUICKLY.
- YEAH, IT WILL,
BUT I'M THINKING
WE SHOULD SHOW
THESE DUDES FIRST HAND
JUST HOW SCARY
NAKED MUMMY CAN BE.
SOUND GOOD TO YOU, BRO?
- ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU JUST SAID?
AND I AGREE WITH YOU.
- SO YOU'RE THINKING
WHAT I'M THINKING...
ABOUT SHOWING THESE HERE BOYS
JUST HOW HORRIFYING--
- LET'S TEACH
THESE GUYS A LESSON!
- ( monkeys screech )
- THESE CLOWNS REALLY NEED
TO DO A LOT OF WORK
ON THE LAME COMEDY ROUTINE.
- YEAH, AND THE WHOLE
"BRO' ACT"
IS KIND OF STRETCH
IF YOU ASK ME.
- ( screaming )
( groaning )
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
- GET ICED!
- ALL RIGHT, FAIRIES.
GET YOURSELVES A TASTE
OF MY MAGIC SHOTGUN!
YOU LIKE THAT?
( gasps )
- ( sizzles )
- ( chuckles )
- THAT REALLY SHOULD
HAVE WORKED BETTER!
( screams )
OWWIE.
- THEY'RE A WHOLE LOT TOUGHER
THAN THEY LOOK.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
- I THOUGHT WE ALREADY
TALKED ABOUT THIS.
OR DIDN'T WE, BRO'?
- BUT THEY'RE A LOT TOUGHER
THAN THEY LOOK, AREN'T THEY?
- JELLAL.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- THAT GUY IS BAD NEWS.
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DO YOU KNOW HIM TOO?
- WELL, IT'S NOT
LIKE WE'RE FRIENDS.
HE TRIED TO KILL ME,
AND ERZA,
AND A BUNCH
OF OTHER PEOPLE.
HE'S THE ONE WHO GOT
THE MAGIC COUNCIL
TO FIRE THE ETHERION CANNON.
- I KNOW.
I HEARD ABOUT THAT.
- BUT I THOUGHT JELLAL
WAS ANCIENT HISTORY.
- HE IS INDEED A SHELL HAUNTED
BY A RESTLESS GHOST,
FULL OF MISERABLE IDEALS.
BUT ALSO A MAN WHO'S GIVEN YOU
THE GREATEST GIFT.
- WHAT? HE DID?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- THIS IS YOUR OPPORTUNITY
TO RETURN THE FAVOR
AND REVIVE HIM.
- DON'T DO IT.
NO MATTER WHAT THIS GUY SAYS,
DON'T WAKE HIM UP.
PLEASE, DON'T DO IT.
YOU CAN'T!
- ( dagger unsheathes )
- SO ARE YOU REFUSING?
- NO, PLEASE, STOP!
( gasps )
- ( metal clinks )
- PLEASE, I BEG YOU.
( whimpers )
- REVIVE HIM.
YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO DO SO.
- NO, THAT'S THE LAST THING
YOU WANT TO DO.
THEY'RE PLANNING TO USE HIM
TO STEAL NIRVANA.
- BUT I HAVE TO REPAY HIM.
I WOULDN'T BE HERE
IF IT WEREN'T FOR HIM.
( cries )
HE WAS SO KIND TO ME.
I'VE HEARD ALL OF THOSE
HORRIBLE STORIES
ABOUT WHAT HE DID.
BUT I DON'T BELIEVE THEM.
- I SWEAR THEY'RE TRUE.
I WAS THERE.  I SAW IT!
- HE'S NOT THE KIND OF PERSON
WHO COULD DO THAT!
- BUT HE DID, WENDY.
- PLEASE, JUST--
JUST GIVE ME A LITTLE TIME
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
- WHY? TELL HIM NO.
- VERY WELL.
YOU HAVE FIVE MINUTES.
- NATSU, I HOPE
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY.
WE REALLY NEED
YOU RIGHT NOW.
- ( gasps )
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THE TERRIFYING
NAKED MUMMY GUILD
WAS DEFEATED
BY TWO PUNY WIZARDS.
- IT'S UNREAL.
NAKED MUMMY WAS TAKEN DOWN
BY THOSE TWO LITTLE GUYS.
- YEAH, I JUST
GOT DONE SAYING THAT
I DIDN'T BELIEVE IT HAPPENED.
- OH, MAN, THAT WAS A WORKOUT.
I THOUGHT IT'D
BE A LOT EASIER.
- THEY PUT UP ONE
HECK OF A FIGHT FOR SURE.
- WHAT KIND OF IDIOT THINKS
TAKING ON AN ENTIRE GUILD
WOULD BE A WALK IN THE PARK?
YOU WERE OUTNUMBERED
20 TO ONE AT LEAST.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU BIG DUMMY.
TELL ME WHERE
YOU GUY'S HIDEOUT IS?
- I AIN'T TELLING YOU SQUAT.
( laughs )
- ( growls )
HOW ABOUT YOU?!
- THESE BOYS ARE SO RECKLESS.
- OKAY, THEY'RE
ALL YOURS, BUDDY,
HAVE AT 'EM.
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- WELL, WELL, I SEE YOU
PESKY LITTLE FLIES
ARE STILL BUZZING AROUND.
THAT'S WHY I'VE BEEN SENT
TO COME SWAT YOU DOWN
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
YOU INSECTS.
- NO.
- NOT THIS GUY AGAIN.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON,
COOL BREEZE?
LONG TIME NO SEE.
HOW YOU BEEN, MAN?
- WHAT?!
WE'RE ENEMIES, YOU FOOL!
- ARE YOU THAT DENSE?
HE WAS BEHIND THE PLOT
TO TAKE OUT GRAMPS AND THE REST
OF THE GUILD MASTERS
WITH THE LULLABY FLUTE,
REMEMBER?!
- OH YEAH! HE'S THE WINDBAG
I ROASTED ON
THAT BRIDGE, RIGHT?
TALK ABOUT A JERK.
- AFTER THE FALL OF
THE EISENWALD GUILD,
I USED MY EXPERTISE
AS AN ENFORCER
IN THE SERVICE OF
THE ORACION SEIS,
BIDING MY TIME UNTIL NOW,
THE DAY THAT I WOULD
FINALLY HAVE MY REVENGE,
THE DAY ERIGOR THE REAPER
WOULD RISE AGAIN!
- SO YOU'VE COME HERE
LOOKING FOR A REMATCH.
IS THAT IT?
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN TO ME.
- WHAT? THOSE TWO KNUCKLEHEADS
ARE GOING TO FIGHT AGAIN?!
RECKLESS DOESN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO DESCRIBE THEM.
- ( screaming )
- AIR MAGIC: AERIAL.
- ( shouting )
- Unicorn #1: I CAN'T BREATHE!
- Unicorn #2: I CAN'T SEE!
- Unicorn #3: I CAN'T HEAR!
- INSIDE THAT DOME,
THE AIR HAS LESS OXYGEN,
WHICH MEANS NONE OF YOU SHOULD
BE ABLE TO STAND EITHER.
- Unicorn #4:
WHAT'S HIS DEAL?
- Unicorn #5: HE JUST GONNA
STAND THERE AND LOOK CUTE?
- Unicorn #6:
LET'S MAKE HIM UGLY!
- I CAN MAKE THINGS
GET REALLY UGLY.
- ( screams )
- SNOW MAGIC: TOTAL WHITEOUT!
YOU'LL BE SNOW BLIND
AND FROZEN IN YOUR TRACKS.
YOU THINK THIS IS CUTE?
- ( shivers, whimpers )
- Unicorn #4: SORRY.
- Unicorn #5:
PLEASE FORGIVE US.
- FOOLISH LAMIA SCALE MEMBERS.
- LET US SHOW YOU REAL MAGIC.
- IS THAT SO?
- BY DRAWING A PICTURE?
- IT'S PICTO MAGIC.
- Red Hood guild:
UNISON PICTO!
- ( chittering )
- WHAT ARE THEY? GOBLINS?
- OH MY GOODNESS, I'M IN LOVE.
- DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
THEY ARE VICIOUS BEASTS.
- ( chittering )
- YOU HAVE
TO FIGHT THEM, SHERRY.
- WOOD DOLL!
- ( crying )
- AWW, THE POOR WITTLE THINGS.
- I SAID, DON'T
LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
- LISTEN TO THE MAN.
- DON'T YOU DARE
TAKE YOUR EYES OFF
THE CUTE LITTLE GOBLINS.
- Red Hood guild:
UNISON PICTO!
- ( screeches )
- IS THAT A WYVERN?!
- HE'S NOT QUITE AS CUTE.
- THEY ARE REMARKABLY
SKILLED ARTISTS.
- DO YOUR WORST, WYVERN.
- CRUSH THOSE NOSY DO-GOODERS.
- ( goblins cry )
- THEIR MAGIC IS STRONG.
- Both: WHAT'LL WE DO?
- IRON ROCK, SPIKES!
HURRY, FINISH HIM!
- ICE MAKE...
- MARIONETTE ATTACK...
- SNOW TIGER!
- ROCK DOLL!
- PRAYING HANDS:
IRON ROCK POWDER EXPLOSION!
- ( roars )
- ( goblins gasp )
- THEY BEAT THE WYVERN
SO QUICKLY.
- CAN WE DRAW SOMETHING SCARIER?
- YOU MAY THINK
THEY ARE JUST DRAWINGS,
BUT I DON'T APPROVE
OF YOUR CARELESS USE
OF LIVING CREATURES
TO DO YOUR DIRTY WORK.
- ( screams )
- I THINK THIS JOKER'S
GONNA BE A MAJOR STEP UP
FROM THAT PACK OF MONKEYS.
- I GOT THIS.
FIRE DRAGON...
- FLY.
- IRON FIST!
- FIRE DOESN'T
REALLY SEEM LIKE
THE BEST WEAPON TO USE
AGAINST WIND, DOES IT?
- YOU WOULDN'T THINK SO.
NATSU MAY HAVE
HAD A TOUGH TIME
BEATING THIS CREEP
IN THEIR LAST FIGHT,
BUT HE'S A LOT STRONGER NOW
THAN HE WAS BACK THEN.
- NO WAY!
- FIRE DRAGON TALON!
- THIS KID IS ON A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT LEVEL THAN BEFORE.
I'VE SEE YOU'VE STEPPED UP
YOUR GAME, LITTLE FLY.
- GLAD YOU NOTICED.
BUT I DON'T HAVE THE TIME
TO CHAT WITH YOU RIGHT NOW.
I'VE GOT TO KICK
YOUR BUTT REAL QUICK
SO I CAN GO AND
RESCUE MY FRIENDS.
- BUT YOU STILL
HAVE A BIG MOUTH.
THIS'LL SHUT YOU UP!
EMERA BARAM!
( laughing )
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THAT,
YOU PEST?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S IMPROVED.
EVER SINCE OUR LAST BATTLE,
I'VE BEEN TRAINING NON-STOP
TO INCREASE MY
DESTRUCTIVE POWERS,
BUILDING MY STRENGTH
TO TAKE YOU DOWN FOR GOOD.
- THAT'S JUST PITIFUL.
IF ALL YOU'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT
IS REVENGE THIS WHOLE TIME,
YOU HAVEN'T GROWN ONE BIT.
- WHAT?!
- Natsu: I GUESS
I SHOULD BE FLATTERED.
I DIDN'T REALIZE I WAS
THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU.
- HMM.
- ( chuckles )
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND A THING.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT WHAT
YOU DID TO EISENWALD
OR ON BEHALF OF
THE ORACION SEIS.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU AT ALL.
IT'S ABOUT ME.
I WON'T BE BEATEN!
- WE'LL JUST SEE ABOUT THAT.
YOU AND ME!
LET'S GO!
I'LL BLOW YOU AWAY!
- MAGIC WIND PALM!
- FLAME LOTUS
FIRE DRAGON FIST!
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- ( weakly )
NO, NOT AGAIN.
- WHY'D YOU HAVE TO DRAG
THAT ONE OUT SO LONG, YOU PYRO?
-  MY, QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
I DIDN'T KNOW THE SALAMANDER
WAS THIS POWERFUL.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU BIG BLOWHARD!
YOU BETTER WAKE UP
AND START TELLING ME
WHERE YOUR CREEPY FRIENDS
TOOK HAPPY AND WENDY!
- OH GEEZ.
- ( thudding )
- WHERE'S
THE ORACION SEIS HIDING?
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
AN "ANCIENT VILLAGE
IN THE WEST?"
- YOU GOT TO LOVE THE IRONY.
THESE HOODED FLUNKIES
THE GUILD SENT TO KEEP US AWAY
ENDED UP TELLING US
EXACTLY WHERE TO FIND THEM.
- I WANT THE TWO OF YOU
TO START HEADING WEST.
- AND YOU?
- AN ENORMOUS MAGICAL FORCE
IS APPROACHING.
- IS IT ONE OF
THE ORACION SEIS?
- MOST LIKELY.
I SHALL REMAIN HERE
AND ENGAGE THEM.
- I HAVE DECIDED
TO SHOW YOU MERCY.
COUNT YOURSELVES LUCKY
TO BE LEAVING
WITH YOUR LIVES
AND LIMBS INTACT.
YOU GUYS COULD RETURN
THE FAVOR, YOU KNOW.
- PUT A SOCK IN IT,
YOU GEEZER.
- I WILL HAVE YOU KNOW
I AM UNDER 30.
- HE SAID "SHUT UP."
- WELL, THEN, LET'S GO.
MAN ON MAN...
A WINNER-TAKE-ALL BRAWL
AND I WON'T HOLD BACK THIS TIME.
OR ARE YOU TOO SCARED OF ME?
- ( sighs )
- I UNDERESTIMATED YOU MEN
AND HELD BACK IN BATTLE.
IT'S QUITE COMPLICATED REALLY.
I CAN ONLY FIGHT
TO MY FULLEST ABILITY
WHEN THERE ARE
BEAUTIFUL LADIES WATCHING.
IT'S LIKE THEY SAY,
"A CLEVER FALCON
IS ONE WHO HIDES HIS TALONS."
- Men: SHUT UP, YOU PIG!
- DO WE REALLY HAVE TO CARRY
THIS GUY ALL THE WAY BACK?
LET'S PUT HIM
OUT OF HIS MISERY.
- WHOEVER YOUR LEADER MAY BE,
I'M SURE
THEY WOULD PREFER
ME IN ONE PIECE.
- LADY ANGEL
SAID SHE FORGOT
TO GET SOME
INFORMATION OUT OF HIM.
- YEAH, WITH THAT FREAKY
COPYING MAGIC SHE USES.
- YUP, SO WE'RE STUCK
WITH HIM FOR NOW.
- MAN!
- IS THIS IT?
HAPPY! WENDY!
- HEY, QUIET!
OUR ENEMY MIGHT BE
HIDING DOWN THERE.
- Natsu:
HAPPY! WENDY!
- NATSU!
- RACER, INTERCEPT THEM.
- GLADLY, BOSS.
- MISERABLE FOOLS.
- WHAT'S THIS GUY
DOING HERE?
- Brain: TIME IS UP.
- ( cries )
- PLEASE DON'T DO IT, WENDY.
- LOOK, YOUR MAGIC
CAN BRING HIM BACK.
SO WILL YOU HELP YOUR FRIEND
OR LEAVE HIM LIKE THIS?
YOU MUST!
- JELLAL.
- I CAN HANDLE THIS DUDE.
YOU NEED TO GET DOWN THERE
AND HELP THEM.
- GOTCHA.
- HA!
YOU'LL STAY RIGHT HERE.
- BUST OUT YOUR WINGS.
COME ON.
- HERE YOU GO.
YOU CAN USE THIS INSTEAD.
- LET'S GO! HA HA!
- ( screams )
- Racer:
YOU GOT SOME NERVE.
NO ONE PUTS THE BRAKES ON ME.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU HAD A LITTLE
PROBLEM WITH TRACTION.
- ( moaning )
- ARE YOU SICK?
- Natsu: HAPPY!
- Carla: WENDY!
- ARE YOU HERE?!
- ANSWER ME, CHILD!
- Happy: NATSU!
- THAT'S HIM.
- THERE, THAT CAVE.
- I CAN DO
A WHOLE LOT MORE THAN JUST
PUT THE BRAKES ON YOU, PAL.
YOU READY?
- NO.
- WHAT?
- BUT HOW?
- NATSU.
- ( smirks )
- ( cries )
I'M SO SORRY.
FORGIVE ME.
( crying )
- Natsu: JELLAL.
- POOR THING.
SHE'S GETTING WORSE.
THE POISON
IS STARTING TO
SPREAD LIKE CRAZY.
HAS ANYBODY BEEN ABLE
TO TRACK DOWN WENDY YET?
- I HAVE NO CLUE.
I CAN'T GET THROUGH TO ANYBODY.
- WHY? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
BUT I PROMISE YOU,
WE'RE GONNA SAVE ERZA.
- I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
PLEASE, JUST HOLD ON.
- Wendy: I'M SORRY.
( cries )
SORRY, SORRY.
BUT I--
I HAD TO.
I OWE HIM.
( cries )
- WENDY, YOU USED YOUR
HEALING MAGIC ON HIM?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT DOES TO YOU.
WENDY!
- I DON'T KNOW WHY YOUR HERE
OR WHERE YOU CAME FROM...
( growls )
BUT YOU DON'T BELONG HERE!
( screams )
- NATSU, NO.
- THANKFULLY YOUR CONDITION
HASN'T DIMINISHED YOUR POWER.
- NATSU!
COME ON,
YOU GOT TO GET UP!
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S ROCK.
BRING IT ON!
- HE JUST LEFT.
- THAT COWARD.
- I'M AWARE THAT THE TWO OF YOU
HAVE SOME KIND OF HISTORY,
BUT OUR FIRST PRIORITY
NEEDS TO BE
TAKING WENDY BACK TO THE OTHERS
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- ( growls )
- YOU DO WANT TO SAVE
YOUR FRIEND, DON'T YOU?
- COME ON.
- MAN, I HATE THAT GUY!
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S GO, OKAY?
- AYE, SIR.
- THAT WAS UNEXPECTED.
BUT PERHAPS
I REMOVED HIS SHACKLES
A BIT PREMATURELY.
THAT'S SAID,
THIS AGGRESSIVE HOSTILITY
HE SEEMS TO HARBOR
TOWARD ME NOW
IS DEFINITELY
A RECENT DEVELOPMENT.
WAS HE AWARE ALL THIS TIME?
DID HE OVERHEAR US
DISCUSSING OUR PLANS
FOR NIRVANA WHILE HE SLEPT?
( gasps )
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
DOES HE INTEND HOARD NIRVANA'S
POWER ALL FOR HIMSELF?
HE MUSTN'T! IT SHOULD
BELONG TO ALL OF US.
I CANNOT ALLOW HIM
TO STEAL OUR POWER.
COBRA, DO YOU HEAR ME?
JELLAL HAS ESCAPED
TO CLAIM NIRVANA.
FIND HIM AND
STOP HIM AT ONCE.
- I HEAR YOU LOUD AND CLEAR,
BOSS MAN.
AS LOUDLY AS I HEAR
THAT COWARDS FOOTSTEPS.
- THIS GUY'S CRAZY FAST.
IT'S NUTS.
- AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'M THE FASTEST MAN ALIVE.
YOU'LL NEVER BEAT ME
'CAUSE YOU'LL NEVER CATCH ME.
THEY CALL ME RACER.
- NATSU FOUND 'EM.
- BUT HOW?  BRAIN WOULD NEVER
LET THEM SLIP AWAY LIKE THAT.
HOW DID THEY GET PAST HIM?!
- THEY PROBABLY JUST
BEAT HIM SENSELESS.
- WELL, END OF THE LINE.
- HEY, LOOK OUT!
- HAPPY! CARLA!
- ( moaning )
- I TOLD YOU IT'S
THE END OF THE LINE.
- ICE MAKE: RAMPART!
- GOT HIM?
- HURRY.
( pants )
I SAID I CAN HANDLE
THIS GUY BY MYSELF.
( pants )
- I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN TELL YOU'VE BURNED THOUGH
A BUNCH OF YOUR POWER.
- JUST GO!
I GOT THIS!
- THANKS, MAN.
- I WON'T LET HIM PASS
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
GO!  ERZA'S LIFE
DEPENDS ON IT!
- OKAY, FINE,
BUT ONCE SHE'S HEALED,
WE'RE COMING
BACK FOR YOU.
- YEAH, I KNOW YOU WILL.
- IMPRESSIVE.
THIS IS THE SECOND TIME
THAT YOU'VE STOPPED ME.
- AND IT'S CERTAINLY
NOT GONNA BE THE LAST.
YOU KNOW ICE HAS THE POWER
TO SLOW EVERYTHING DOWN,
DON'T YOU?
WHEN I'M THROUGH, YOU'RE
GONNA BE REALLY SLOW, PAL
'CAUSE I'M GONNA FREEZE YOU
DEAD IN YOUR TRACKS FOREVER.
- ERZA.
- (end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: I CAN'T BELIEVE
GRAY'S TRYING
TO HOG ALL THE FUN.  I BET
HE THINKS HE LOOKS COOL, HUH?
HE REALLY BURNS ME UP SOMETIMES.
- Happy: DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
HE'S NOT TRYING TO LOOK COOL
HE'S PUTTING HIMSELF AT RISK
TO HELP US SAVE ERZA.
- BUT HE'S GONNA LOOK COOL
IF HE BEATS
THAT LONG-NOSED SPEEDBALL.
WE CAN'T LET HIM
TAKE ALL THE CREDIT.
- WE'VE GOT
SOMETHING WAY MORE
IMPORTANT TO DO, DUMMY.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
I BET THEIR FIGHT'S OVER
BY THE TIME WE GET THERE ANYWAY.
- IN THAT CASE, I'LL JUST HAVE
TO GO A ROUND WITH GRAY MYSELF.
- WHAT? THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE AT ALL.