- LORD ZEREF.
AT LAST, I HAVE YOU
ALL TO MYSELF.
MY FREEDOM.
AND NO ONE CAN
TAKE YOU AWAY FROM ME.
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU
THE RULER OF THIS WORLD.
AND THEN YOU WILL
BRING ABOUT MY SALVATION.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( explosion )
- ( panting )
- ( growls )
- I DON'T THINK
HE'S GONNA LET US GO.
IF HE CATCHES US,
WE'RE THROUGH.
- ( Elfman groans )
- DON'T STOP.
ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL US?
END OF THE LINE, HUH?
- OH, LOOK AT THAT VIEW.
- I'M SO SWITCHING SIDES.
- Happy:
"ARC OF EMBODIMENT"!
- I'VE HAD IT
UP TO HERE WITH YOU!
WHAT KIND OF LAMEBRAINED BUFFOON
RUNS FOR HIS LIFE
WITHOUT EVEN BOTHERING ONCE
TO LOOK WHERE HE'S RUNNING?!
- YOU LOVE COMPLAINING,
DON'T YOU?
IF THAT'S HOW
YOU WANT TO BE,
YOU CAN GO THE REST
OF THE WAY ON YOUR OWN.
- SO NOT ONLY
ARE YOU AN IDIOT,
YOU'D ALSO LEAVE
A CRIPPLED COMRADE
TO FEND FOR HERSELF?!
- YOU LOOK HEALTHY
AS A HORSE TO ME!
- NOT GOOD.
HE'S GOT US CORNERED.
AND IF HE GOES BERSERK
THIS CLOSE TO THE EDGE,
WE'LL BE MAKING CRATERS
IN NO TIME.
I'M SO LOW ON MAGIC POWER,
I'M NOT EVEN SURE
I COULD FLY.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I DIDN'T
THINK OF THAT BEFORE.
- YOU? THINKING?
NOT A CHANCE.
- THOSE SMARTY-PANTS SPECS
REALLY COME IN HANDY.
I SHOULD GET A PAIR.
- THEY HAVE NOTHING TO DO
WITH MY INTELLIGENCE.
I'M SMART WITH
OR WITHOUT THEM.
OR DID YOU FORGET
THAT YOU'RE TALKING
TO ONE OF THE GREATEST FAIRIES--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT.
- ( screams )
- Elfman:
EYES FORWARD, FREAK SHOW.
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR ME?
- ( growls )
- I'M READY TO THROW DOWN
IF YOU ARE, UGLY.
AND I WON'T HOLD BACK
SO GIVE ME YOUR BEST SHOT.
TAKE OVER BEAST SOUL!
HE FELL FOR IT.
- ( growls )
- Evergreen: ALL RIGHT, YOU.
- YO.
GOOD WORK.
WE TOTALLY FOOLED--
( grunts )
- NEXT TIME YOU COME UP
WITH A PLAN,
LEAVE ME OUT OF IT.
I AM NOT BAIT!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?!
- SLIPPING! I'M SLIPPING!
- A HEATED DISCUSSION FOLLOWED
BY INTENSE PHYSICAL CONTACT?
TODAY'S LOVERS HAVE
NO SENSE OF SHAME, DO THEY?
- Both: SHUT UP!
- ( gasps )
- I'M IMPRESSED.
MANY HAVE MET THEIR END
BY MY BEAST.
SURVIVING THE THUNDER CLAP
IS A FEAT WORTHY
OF HEROIC SONG.
IT WAS A TRULY SHOCKING
TURN OF EVENTS TO SAY THE LEAST,
FINDING VICTORY AFTER
SUCH A PITIFUL DISPLAY.
AND I DO MEAN PITIFUL.
WHERE WAS YOUR GRACEFULNESS?
MY POET'S SOUL
WEPT IN DISGUST.
WIZARDS LIKE YOU
ARE THE SOURCE OF MY IRE.
SCUM LIKE YOU CANNOT
BE PERMITTED.
THE GRAND MAGIC WORLD
WILL SNUFF YOU OUT.
AND THEN JUST LIKE THAT,
WE'LL BE FOREVER FREE.
- YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
A COWARD'S FREEDOM.
A REAL MAN DOESN'T NEED
TO DESTROY THE WORLD
JUST TO FEEL COMFORTABLE
LIVING IN IT.
- ( gasps )
- DON'T YOU GET IT?
MOST PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD
DON'T HAVE MAGIC POWER.
YOU'D PUT THEM THROUGH HELL
AND WIPE THEM OUT
JUST FOR YOUR "FREEDOM."
- THAT'S RIGHT. IF THE GRAND
MAGIC WORLD IS TO BE BORN,
THEY CANNOT BE
ALLOWED TO LIVE.
- I'M NOT GONNA
LET YOU DO THAT, BUB.
- YOU HONESTLY THINK
THEY'RE NECESSARY?
TELL ME WHAT GREAT PURPOSE
DO THEY SERVE?
PEOPLE WHO CAN'T USE MAGIC
ARE LIKE CANDLES
THAT CAN'T BE LIT.
THEY SHOULD BE DISCARDED.
- HAVING MAGIC POWER
DOESN'T MEAN YOUR MORE VALUABLE
THAN SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T.
ALL LIFE HAS MEANING!
( groans )
- OH NO, HE'S INJURED.
BELCUSAS MUST HAVE DONE MORE
DAMAGE TO HIM THAN I THOUGHT.
- WHY DO YOU CARE?
AFRAID TO LOSE
YOUR CASH CROP?
THAT'S A FINE EXAMPLE
OF HYPOCRISY.
YOU CALL ME A COWARD,
BUT IN THE END,
YOU'RE AFRAID OF BEING
LEFT WITH NOTHING.
HOW PATHETIC.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
WE WORK TOGETHER TO MAKE
LIFE EASIER FOR EVERYONE.
IN EXCHANGE FOR OUR SERVICES,
THEY GIVE US COMPENSATION.
THAT RELATIONSHIP
AND TRUST
BUILT THE WORLD
WE LIVE IN.
IT GAVE BIRTH
TO THE GUILDS.
I WON'T LET YOU MOCK
WHAT WE'VE MADE TOGETHER.
THIS WORLD BELONGS
TO EVERYONE!
AND I'LL BE DAMNED
IF I'M GONNA
LET YOU TEAR IT DOWN!
- HOW SAD.
YOU DON'T EVEN REALIZE
YOU'VE ALREADY LOST THE WAR.
YOU'VE STRAYED TOO FAR
FROM THE ABYSS OF SORCERY,
THE INFINITE VOID
FROM WHICH TRUE POWER FLOWS
INEXORABLY AND ETERNALLY.
ZEREF'S POWER ELUDES
YOUR FEEBLE MIND NOW,
BUT YOU WILL LEARN
THAT LESSON SOON,
AS WILL ALL WIZARDS.
AND THE ONLY OPTIONS LEFT
WILL BE SERVITUDE OR THE GRAVE.
- IF THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK,
YOU'VE GOT A WORLD
OF DISAPPOINTMENT AHEAD!
IF FAIRY TAIL'S
HEADING FOR THE GRAVE,
WE'RE TAKING
GRIMOIRE HEART WITH US!
STARTING WITH YOU!
- MY, WHAT AN ELEGANT LANGUAGE.
BUT AT LEAST YOU'VE MADE
YOUR POSITION CLEAR.
- ( groans )
- VERY WELL.
IF YOU WISH
TO ACT LIKE GARBAGE,
THEN YOU SHALL BE
DISPOSED OF ACCORDINGLY.
- LEAVE HIM ALONE!
- YOU CAN CALL ME GARBAGE
IF YOU WANT,
BUT YOU SURE AS HELL
WON'T GET AWAY
WITH TRASH-TALKING
MY FRIENDS!
AS A REAL MAN,
I WON'T LET YOU!
- OH, IS THAT SO?
- NO, ELFMAN!
HMM.
( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
I GOT YOU NOW.
TO OVERCOME AN OPPONENT,
YOU GOT TO LEARN 'EM
INSIDE AND OUT FIRST.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT, BIG SIS?
( groans )
THANKS, PAL.
I NEEDED AN ARM.
- HOW DARE YOU TAINT MY WEAPON
WITH YOUR STENCH.
- YOU READY TO DIE?
- IN MY LEFT HAND APPEARS
A KITE SHIELD
THROUGH WHICH NO ATTACK
SHALL EVER PASS.
YOUR CHEAP TACTIC
HAS FAILED.
NOW WHAT WILL YOU DO?
- ( chuckles )
WHAT'S WRONG, PRETTY BOY.
DON'T FEEL SECURE
WITHOUT YOUR SPECS ON?
DO IT, EVER!
- I DON'T LET MANY PEOPLE
CALL BE BY THAT NICKNAME,
SAVE LAXUS AND THE MEMBERS
OF THE THUNDER LEGION,
BUT I'M IN A GOOD MOOD.
SO I GUESS I CAN
MAKE AN EXCEPTION THIS ONCE.
- ( gasps )
- TURNING THIS DRAMA-CLUB REJECT
INTO A PIGEON PERCH WILL BE
THE HIGHLIGHT OF MY DAY.
NO ONE TRASH-TALKS
FAIRY TAIL AND LIVES.
- NO!
- STONE EYE!
- OH, NO!
( screams )
DRAMA-CLUB REJECT, YOU SAY?
AHEM.
- ( gasps )
AHH!
- ELFMAN!
UGH!
WHY DIDN'T
MY STONE-EYE SPELL WORK?
- UHH, EVER!
- ( footsteps approach )
- HUH?
- SUCH A SHAME.
I HAD HOPED
YOUR LOVER'S BOND
WOULD SOMEHOW MOVE ME.
ALAS, IT SEEMS
NOT EVEN A LOVE
BORN ON THE BATTLEFIELD
CAN MAKE
MY POET'S SOUL QUIVER.
THAT'S NOT TO SAY
THE SHOW WASN'T ENJOYABLE.
- YOUR GLASSES!
I CRUSHED THEM
WITH MY OWN HANDS.
- MY MAGIC IS THAT
OF IMAGINATION,
THE ARC OF EMBODIMENT.
IF I CAN ENVISION IT,
I CAN GIVE IT SHAPE
AND MAKE IT A REALITY.
- WHAT? BUT HOW?
THERE'S NO SUCH POWER.
- THE EMBODIMENT OF WISHES
IS LINKED TO
THE ROOT OF SORCERY.
WHILE IT HAS
ITS LIMITATIONS,
I'D SAY THEY ARE
A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR I POSSESS MAGIC
THAT IS UNMATCHED IN POWER.
AND TO THIS DAY,
IT HAS NEVER BEEN VANQUISHED
BY ANOTHER WIZARD.
- ( growls )
- COME FORTH,
MY DARK TOWER OF DINGIR!
- ( rumbling )
- ( screaming )
- TURN ALL YOUR SORROW
ONTO THE FOOLISH FAIRIES
AND RETURN THEM TO THE REFUSE
FROM WHENCE THEY CAME.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS THING?
I CAN'T MOVE.
- ( voice breaks )
ELFMAN, I--
- EVER, YOU GOT
TO HANG IN THERE.
- I'M SORRY.
- WHAT?
- IF ONLY I HADN'T BEEN
YOUR PARTNER,
YOU MIGHT HAVE BECOME
AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE LOST
OR BEEN HELD BACK
BY A WEAKLING LIKE ME.
- YOU IDIOT.
I MADE IT THIS FAR BECAUSE
YOU WERE BY MY SIDE.
- ( sobs )
ELFMAN.
- I'M GLAD
YOU'RE HERE, EVER.
- NOW WANE TO
THE ENDS OF DARKNESS.
- ( rumbling )
- ( no audio )
- ( groans )
- NATSU!
- YOU'RE ALIVE!
( giggles )
- WHERE'S GRAMPS?
- RIGHT HERE.
- BUT I AM AFRAID
HE ISN'T OUT
OF THE WOODS YET.
- ( growls )
HUH?
MY SCARF'S FIXED.
- WENDY USED HER SKY MAGIC
TO GET THE BAD GUNK OUT.
SHE ALSO FLIPPED
YOUR CLOTHES BACK
WHILE YOU WERE CATNAPPING.
- I OWE YOU ONE.  THANKS.
- NO PROB.
- HMM?
- IS SOMETHING WRONG, NATSU?
- HMM.
( sniffs )
- UM, HELLO?
- GET YOUR SLIMY NOSTRILS
AWAY FROM HER,
YOU FIRE-BREATHING PERVERT!
- AH!
- I KNOW THIS SMELL.
- WHAT SMELL?
PLEASE TELL ME IT'S FISH.
- IT HAS TO BE HIM.
BUT WHY WOULD HE
BE ON THE ISLAND?
- WHO IS HE TALKING ABOUT?
- WENDY, CAN YOU
SMELL IT TOO?
- UH, NOT REALLY.  SORRY.
THERE'RE SO MANY
NEW SCENTS OUT HERE
I'M HAVING TROUBLE
FIGURING OUT WHO'S WHO.
- NATSU, WHO'D YOU
CATCH A WHIFF OF?
JELLAL?
- NO, IT'S THE GUY WE MET
ON GALUNA ISLAND.
- Narrator: YOU MAY REMEMBER
THIS SHORT-STATURED MAN
WITH AN AFFINITY FOR MASKS.
HE WENT BY THE NAME ZALTI
DURING THE GALUNA ISLAND
INCIDENT
WHERE HE CONSPIRED TO OBTAIN
THE POWER OF DELIORA,
A DESTRUCTIVE DEMON
FROM THE BOOK OF ZEREF.
AFTER BEING
DEFEATED BY NATSU,
HE WAS NEVER SEEN AGAIN.
- ( gasps )
HE'S CLOSE.
- Happy: NATSU, WAIT!
- Wendy: DON'T JUST RUN OFF!
- WELL, THERE'S NO POINT
IN TRYING TO STOP HIM.
- WHAT HAPPENED
ON GALUNA ISLAND?
WHO'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
- OH, YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE.
STUFF HAPPENED AND THEN
HE HAD AN ALL-OUT
MAGIC BRAWL WITH THE GUY.
- DO YOU THINK
HE WANTS REVENGE?
- I'M MORE CONCERNED ABOUT
ALL THIS LOST MAGIC BUSINESS.
- I MUST ADMIT I'M ENVIOUS
OF NATSU'S POWERFUL SNOUT.
HE'S JUST LIKE AN ANIMAL.
- Carla: WELL, IT IS NATSU.
- Pantherlily:
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT, HUH?
- Happy: PRETTY MUCH.
- ( heavy breathing )
( muffled ) THIS IS
A STICKY SITUATION.
I CAN'T FIND LORD ZEREF,
MY TEAMMATES ARE GONE,
AND MY APPETITE
IS OUT OF CONTROL.
I NOW THAT I'M EATING,
MY SWEET TOOTH IS BEGGING
FOR A SUGARY TREAT TIDE IT OVER.
LUCKILY I PREPARED
FOR THIS VERY THING.
THIS'LL BE GLORIOUS.
I'VE BEEN WAITING ALL DAY
JUST TO TASTE YOU.
COME TO PAPA,
ICE CREAM CONE.
NO!
- Lahar: LOOK ALIVE, PEOPLE.
GET THE WOUNDED TO THE TENTS
ALONG THE REEF AT ONCE.
WE MUST HEAL THEM QUICKLY.
WE'LL WORRY ABOUT REPAIRS
ONCE WE'VE SECURED THE ISLAND.
- Narrator:
REMEMBER THIS MAN
FROM THE ORACION SEIS
INCIDENT?
HE IS LAHAR,
CAPTAIN OF THE MAGIC COUNCIL'S
FOURTH CUSTODY
ENFORCEMENT UNIT.
A SERIOUS BUNCH
TO SAY THE LEAST.
AFTER NIRVANA HAD
BEEN DEALT WITH,
LAHAR WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR ARRESTING
THE REVIVED FUGITIVE JELLAL.
AND NOW HE'S IN COMMAND
OF THE COUNCIL'S BATTLE FLEET,
MONITORING THE SITUATION
ON TENROU ISLAND.
- WE'RE GOING TO LAUNCH
A FULL ASSAULT ON THE ISLAND.
IF YOU CAN HOLD A WEAPON--
- ( gasps )
- DORANBOLT!
- Narrator:
IT WAS RECENTLY REVEALED
THAT THIS MAN,
LIKE LAHAR, ALSO WORKS
FOR NEW MAGIC COUNCIL.
THOUGH HE WENT
BY THE NAME MEST
WHEN APPEARING TO
THE MEMBERS OF FAIRY TAIL,
HIS ACTUAL NAME
IS DORANBOLT.
HE IS A MEMBER OF THE COUNCIL'S
INTELLIGENCE OFFICE
AND IS QUITE AMBITIOUS.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN PUT THROUGH
A MEAT GRINDER.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
HOW'RE THE CREW MEMBERS?
- THEY'RE ALL FINE.
WE HAD A FEW INJURIES,
BUT THANKFULLY
NO SIGNIFICANT CASUALTIES.
- WHAT ABOUT
THE COMMUNICATION LACRIMA?
- IT STILL WORKS.
NOW CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED OUT THERE?
- I WAS MAKING PROGRESS.
NEXT THING I KNOW--
A THREE-WAY WAR
BETWEEN FAIRY TAIL,
GRIMOIRE HEART, AND ZEREF
EXPLODES IN MY FACE.
THE ATTACK ON THE SHIPS
WAS GRIMOIRE HEART'S DIRTY WORK.
WHERE IS
THE COMMUNICATION LACRIMA?
THE COUNCIL NEEDS TO KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
- THIS CAN'T BE COINCIDENCE!
THE BIGGEST THORNS
IN OUR SIDE
SOMEHOW WIND UP GATHERED
AT THE SAME PLACE.
IF I WERE A GAMBLING MAN,
I'D SAY THIS GAME WAS RIGGED.
THE CHAIRMAN WON'T HESITATE.
YOU KNOW HOW HE IS:
AS RIGID AS STEEL AND SWIFT
TO CARRY OUT JUDGMENT.
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY LIKE THIS
IN FRONT OF HIM,
HE MAY JUST DECIDE
TO WIPE THEM OUT.
- AN ETHERION BLAST?!
- IF THE CHAIRMAN DOES
RESORT TO THAT,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO OBEY.
- OUT OF THE QUESTION!
I KNOW THAT
THE COUNCIL'S HAD IT IN
FOR FAIRY TAIL
FOR A LONG TIME NOW,
BUT THEY DON'T DESERVE
THE SAME FATE
AS ZEREF OR GRIMOIRE HEART.
- IF I'M ORDERED
TO EXECUTE THEM,
THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
- ( gasps )
- ( no audio )
- NOW WILL YOU TELL
H.Q. OR SHALL I?
- WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT IS GENOCIDE.
- ONLY 10% OF THE POPULATION
WILL BE ALLOWED TO LIVE?
- YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT WILL WORK?
PEOPLE WILL
FIGHT TO THE END
TILL THERE'S NO WORLD LEFT.
- PERHAPS.
THEN AGAIN, HADES
HAS YET TO REVEAL
THE FULL EXTENT OF HIS PLAN.
HE DREAMS OF A HEAVEN
FOR THOSE ATTUNED
WITH THE ABYSS OF SORCERY.
THE BLACK WIZARD
WILL BE OURS.
AND ONCE HE IS, THE WORLD
YOU KNOW WILL VANISH.
ONCE ALL THE FIRE
AND DUST HAVE SETTLED,
IT WILL BE REBORN.
- YOU TALK TOO MUCH.
ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS MAKING YOU PAY DEARLY
FOR COMING INTO OUR HOUSE
AND ACTING LIKE
YOU OWN THE PLACE.
- MY COMRADES AND I
HAVE TWO MISSIONS.
THE FIRST
IS TO SEIZE ZEREF
AND THEN DELIVER HIM SAFELY
TO MASTER HADES.
AND THE SECOND ONE IS
TO WIPE FAIRY TAIL
FROM EXISTENCE.
- YOU THINK YOU CAN
WIPE US OUT?
LET'S PUT THAT THEORY
TO THE TEST.
- WAIT.
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- COVERING YOUR RETREAT.
SINCE HE'S JUST ONE
OF THE SEVEN KIN,
IT'S SAFE TO SAY
THERE'S A SIX PACK OF NASTY
SOMEWHERE OUT THERE.
I'LL HOLD HIM OFF
WHILE YOU HUNT DOWN
THE REST OF HIS CREW.
- DO YOU GOT A SCREW LOOSE?
THE FOUR OF US COMBINED
COULDN'T TAKE HIM DOWN
AND YOU WANT TO GO
SOLO ON HIM?
- THAT'S BECAUSE HIS MAGIC
WAS SAPPING YOUR STRENGTH.
HUMAN ENSLAVEMENT MAGIC,
IT'S ANCIENT
AND POWERFUL STUFF.
- HUMAN ENSLAVEMENT?
- Loke: IT'S ALSO
KNOWN AS RULER'S MAGIC.
IT TEMPORARILY REDUCES
THE COMBAT ABILITIES
AND MAGIC POWER
OF ANY HUMAN IT AFFECTS.
CELESTIAL SPIRITS
ARE IMMUNE TO IT,
SO WE CAN FIGHT EVENLY.
YOU MAY HAVE ALREADY
FIGURED THIS OUT,
BUT HE'S ALSO
CELESTIAL SPIRIT.
CAPRICORN, THE SEA GOAT.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
- SERIOUSLY?
- THIS IS BAD.
CELESTIAL SPIRITS
FIGHTING EACH OTHER?
I CAN'T LET THAT
HAPPEN AGAIN.
WE'LL STAY HERE AND HELP.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
HOW ABOUT IT, SEA GOAT,
FEEL LIKE GOING TOE-TO-TOE
WITH A SUPERIOR FIGHTER?
LET'S DO THIS.
- I ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
TO BE HONEST, LEO,
I WAS BEGINNING TO WONDER
WHETHER YOU
REMEMBERED THAT
YOU WERE
A CELESTIAL SPIRIT.
- GET OUT OF HERE.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
- WE CAN'T.
- I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
LUCY, BUT HE'S RIGHT.
- WE'RE JUST A BURDEN
WITHOUT OUR FULL MAGIC POWER.
LOKE KNOWS WHAT
HE'S GOT TO DO NOW.
SO LET'S MAKE SURE
THAT HE CAN.
- LOKE!
- DON'T WORRY, BEAUTIFUL.
I GOT THIS FIGHT
IN THE BAG.
JUST FOCUS ON FINDING THE OTHERS
AND STOPPING THEM.
- YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME
TO LEAVE YOU HERE
TO FIGHT ONE
OF YOUR OWN KIND.
- GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
- I GET THE FEELING
THERE'S MORE TO THIS FIGHT
THAN LOKE'S
WILLING TO TELL US.
- THERE'S DEFINITELY
SOME BAD BLOOD
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM
TIME FOR US TO GO.
SO COME ON.
YOU HAVE FAITH IN HIM, RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT THEN,
WE GOT TO HURRY.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE OTHERS.
- ( sighs )
- Lucy: LOKE!
WIN THIS.
PLEASE PROMISE
YOU'LL COME BACK
SAFE AND SOUND.
PROMISE ME!
- Gray: LUCY!
- ( gasps )
I KNOW THAT FACE.
- YOU'VE GOT BIGGER THINGS
TO WORRY ABOUT AT THE MOMENT.
( grunts )
JUST HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
SINCE YOU LEFT
THE CELESTIAL SPIRIT WORLD?
- 17 YEARS.
- THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'VE MANAGED
TO LAST THAT LONG
ON YOUR OWN POWER.
TELL ME WHO ARE YOU
CONTRACTED TO?!
- NO HUMAN CONTROLS ME,
BUT I HAVE PLENTY
OF SERVANTS OF MY OWN.
COME FORTH,
MIGHTY HERO OF RUBENGALD.
- ( gasps )
AN OTHERWORLDLY GATE?
- SAN ZHAO XIN.
- ( gasps )
HE'S NOT
A CELESTIAL SPIRIT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Caprico:
GENERAL SAN ZHAO XIN
LED THE ANTI-GOVERNMENT FORCES
TO VICTORY
DURING THE RUBENGALD CIVIL WAR
IN THE YEAR 779.
HE WENT MISSING
SHORTLY AFTER,
BUT THE TRUTH
OF THE MATTER
IS HE BECAME MY SLAVE.
HE LIVES AND DIES
BY MY WILL.
- YOU'VE GONE OVER THE EDGE.
KEEPING HUMANS AS PUPPETS
IS BARBARIC.
- AND BEING A SLAVE TO
YOUR OWNER IS SOMEHOW NOBLE?
- MY OWNER HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
- I WONDER.  WHO EXACTLY
IS HOLDING YOUR LEASH?
MIGHT IT BE THAT BLONDE GIRL
YOU TOLD TO FLEE.
SHE SEEMED
QUITE FOND OF YOU.
YOU NEVER WANTED TO
CHALLENGE ME TO A DUEL.
DID YOU, LEO?
THIS WAS JUST A WAY
OF GETTING HER TO SAFETY
WHILE FOOLING ME--
A CLEVER TACTIC.
BEING A PUPPET IS SUCH
A THANKLESS ROLE TO PLAY.
SUCH A BORING EXISTENCE.
- WIN THIS.
PLEASE PROMISE
YOU'LL COME BACK
SAFE AND SOUND.
PROMISE ME!
- ( gasps )
- Woman: DEAR CAPRICORN.
PLEASE PROMISE YOU'LL
COME BACK SAFE AND SOUND.
PROMISE ME.
- THAT GIRL.
SHE COULDN'T POSSIBLY... NO!
- HE FIGURED IT OUT!
- I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO, LEO!
WHY YOU'RE
PROTECTING THAT ONE!
I SHOULD'VE SEEN IT BEFORE!
THE RESEMBLANCE IS UNCANNY.
SHE'S THE DAUGHTER
OF LAYLA HEARTFILIA.
- HERE IT GOES.
IT'S TIME TO BUST OUT
THE BIG GUNS!
- WHERE DID YOU SEND HER?!
SHE CAN'T BE ALLOWED TO LIVE!
- HE'S CLOSE.
I CAN SMELL HIM LIKE
HE'S RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
- I GOT A QUESTION
FOR YOU, NATSU.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE
IT'S THE SAME GUY
FROM GALUNA ISLAND
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- THERE WAS SOMETHING
UNIQUE ABOUT HIM.
- YEAH, THAT MASK HE WORE
WAS PRETTY GNARLY.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
- SO WHEN YOU SAY
YOU CAN SMELL HIM
IS IT 'CAUSE OF THE SWEAT
INSIDE HIS MASK?
- NO, THAT'S JUST DISGUSTING!
WOULD YOU QUIT
GOOFING OFF ALREADY?
THIS IS SERIOUS.
- Narrator: JUST WHO IS ZALTI?
AND WHY HAS HE COME
TO TENROU ISLAND OF ALL PLACES?
- ( theme music plays )
- LORD ZEREF,
WITH YOU,
I WILL CREATE A NEW FUTURE.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: MAN, ALL THESE SHEEP
ARE MAKING ME SLEEPY.
- Happy: HUH? WHAT ABOUT SHEEP?
- Natsu:
I MEAN CELESTIAL SPIRITS.
ISN'T THE SHY, FLUFFY SPIRIT
THAT LUCY HAS A SHEEP?
OR AM I DUMB?
- Happy: YES, ARIES IS A SHEEP.
AND, YES, YOU ARE DUMB. - Natsu:
AND THE GUY LOKE'S FIGHTING
IS A SHEEP TOO, RIGHT? ARE THEY
TWIN SPIRITS OR SOMETHING?
- Happy: NO, HE'S A GOAT.
THEY'RE TOTALLY
DIFFERENT FROM SHEEP.
- Natsu: OKAY,
SO WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
- Happy:
WELL, SHEEP GO, "BAAH."
WHILE GOATS YOU USUALLY
SOUND LIKE "BEEH."
GOT IT?
- Natsu: RIGHT.
AND I'M THE DUMB ONE.