[LUCY]
This is Crocus,
the bustling, flower-blooming
capital of the Fiore Kingdom!
A city that once
again finds itself
hosting the annual
Grand Magic Games.
It's time to see the
kingdom's wizard guilds
competing for the coveted
title of "Fiore's finest"!
[LUCY] The glowing palace
of lights, Mercurius,
shines as the crown jewel
in the heart of it all.
Atop a craggy mountain
to the west
stands the true
home of the games,
the Domus Flau coliseum.
And this fabulous
little apartment
is where I call home these days.
At 80,000 Jewel,
it's a bit pricier than
my place in Magnolia.
But the location can't be beat!
So many shops and cafes nearby.
It's a like whole new exciting
world has opened up for me!
Good morning, world.
It's time to face
a brand new day.
I miss my old place sometimes,
all those peaceful mornings.
Just me alone with my thoughts.
Till I walk into
the living room.
Come on!
Well, no time for moping around!
Flowers can't bloom
without water, right?
[LUCY chuckles]
[PLUE gibbers]
And they can't grow without
a little stretching.
[PLUE cries]
[yelping]
[LUCY humming]
Everything's so fresh here.
This fruit is amazing.
Plus, it does wonders
for my skin!
[PLUE gibbers]
[LUCY] All right, gotta
look extra cute today!
[LUCY]
All done!
Now it's time for
me to go to work!
[PLUE gibbers]
[NARRATOR] It is now 792,
one year has passed
since humanity's epic battle
against the Demons of Tartaros.
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's going to be a
thrilling day four
of the 792 Grand Magic Games!
Greetings! Howdy, folks,
it's Chapati Lola again.
Joining me here is Former
Member of the Magic Council
and Fiore's current
favorite celebrity chef!
That man is Mr. Yajima!
Good to be here.
So are we ready to see
some heart-stopping
battles of wizardry?
Oh crap, it's already
getting started!
I need to see a
valid pass, please.
Huh? Oh, right!
Wait, i-it's in here.
At least, I hope it's in here.
We can't let you through
without a proper ID, miss.
[LUCY]
Can't you make an exception?
No exceptions.
[LUCY]
Aw, come on. Please?
I just said "no exceptions."
I get your point, okay?
[LUCY] Well, if words
don't do the trick.
[LUCY] Umm, I know that it'd be
bending the rules a little bit,
but I won't tattle on you.
[giggles]
[BOTH]
No exceptions!
Have it your way, jerks!
[GUARD A]
What was that?
[LUCY] Okay, I'll just have to
use more brain than beauty!
Whoa!
--[GUARD B] Hey! Get back here!
--[GUARD A] Stop! Gotcha!
Hands off of me!
You ever heard of freedom
of the press? Let go!
Whaddaya know?
[CHAPATI] Now let's get into the
first match of the semi-finals!
After dominating
the earlier rounds,
it's no surprise to see
Chrisark of Duallahan Head
enter the coliseum!
Yo-ho-ho!
[CHAPATI] Will he continue
his winning streak today?
Or will Berick of Dwarf
Gear shut him down?
Whatever happens, it's sure
to be an amazing battle!
Well, Mr. Yajima, your thoughts?
What should we keep an
eye on in this match?
I suppose it'd be wise to say
that we should keep
both eyes on the match.
Yeah, but for what?
This Chrisark fellow is
a truly powerful wizard,
and seemingly without equal.
If you were to blink,
you could very well
miss the entire match.
[JASON gasping]
Cool! Cool!
Aw, man, I am stoked for
these semifinals! So cool!
Hey, boss! So sorry I'm late!
[JASON]
Hmm.
I kinda got held up.
Lucy.
You're looking so cool!
As per usjze!
That was the idea!
Has the match started yet?
[JASON]
No, not quite yet.
But I think it's about to be
over if Chrisark keeps his cool.
No matter what happens,
we'll be here to tell the story!
Cool!
[LUCY] It's crazy how
much things have changed
in the last year.
New place, new city,
and a new job as an editor
at Sorcerer Weekly!
"Editor-in-training" actually.
[LUCY] Literally the very next
day after Natsu and Happy
left for their training mission,
Master Makarov
disbanded the guild.
Although I tried to believe
it wasn't really happening,
it was true.
I was devastated.
It was like losing my family.
Everyone had to pick up the
pieces and go our separate ways.
The others seemed so hopeful
about what the future
had in store for them.
Just like the master said,
it was "time to follow
our own paths."
It took a while for me
to accept what happened.
So I may have gotten
a late start on that.
But one day Jason came
to me with a job.
A modeling job...
[PHOTOGRAPHER A]
Nice!
Cool pose!
[LUCY]
I was apprehensive at first,
but I guess I must've
impressed him
because he kept on hiring me.
[JASON] The last feature
was a huge success,
so I wanna push the
envelope even further!
Yeah?
Okay.
Tentacles off me, pal!
This is so much cooler
than I thought it'd be!
Check out that action!
[yelping]
[PHOTOGRAPHER A]
Nice!
Cool beans!
All right, everybody,
that's a wrap for today!
Let's clear the set!
Thanks for calling
again, you guys.
Of course.
You'll do just about
anything, won't ya?
What do you think about modeling
exclusively for The Sorce?
Well, I, uh--
Honestly...
It's always been my biggest
dream to be a writer.
Wait, do you mean like
stories and stuff?
I do.
How cool! That's great!
You should totally
give it a shot sometime!
Really? You'd hire me
to write for you guys?
Oh, yeah!
Hang on. You mean us?
Yes!
I have read Sorcerer
Weekly every single week
for as long as I can remember.
The photography and the
articles are really inspiring.
Writing for such
a great magazine
would be a dream come true!
And I promise you won't
be disappointed in me!
Pretty please?
[JASON]
Hmm...
I don't know.
[LUCY] I'll give it
everything I've got!
Well...
Okay.
I guess I could be cool
and ask my bosses
if they'll hire you on.
[LUCY]
That would be uber cool!
[JASON]
But if we do hire you,
it'd have to be as an
editor-in-training.
[LUCY gasps]
Oh, that sounds like an
amazing opportunity!
I swear, I won't let you down!
[JASON]
I gotta warn ya first.
Our models are treated
extremely well by the company.
But a lowly trainee is a
different story altogether.
You understand?
You'll be on the bottom rung.
It's brutal down there.
Yeah, I understand.
And I realize it won't be easy!
[PHOTOGRAPHER A]
Nice! Nice!
Nice!
So hot! I mean, so cool!
[PHOTOGRAPHER A] All right,
everybody, that's a wrap.
Let's clear the set!
Thank you so much!
Cool!
Hm?
Lucy! Robe! Now!
Uh, yes, sir!
[JASON]
You forgot her drink!
[LUCY]
Yes, sir!
[JASON]
Prep for the interview!
Right!
Hey, uh, I hope you don't mind,
but I thought of a couple of
questions for today's interview.
Not in a million years.
Sorry.
[JASON]
Hmm.
I'm startin' to sweat
over my deadline,
but this article is crap.
[LUCY]
Umm.
This might be presumptuous,
but here, I put
something together.
[LUCY]
What do you think?
I dunno. It reads more like
a novel than a puff piece.
[LUCY]
Huh?
Not in a thousand years!
Oh.
That's a whole lot better
than a million, I guess!
I'll rewrite it!
Now hold on a minute.
First you gotta book us a
photographer and stylist
for tomorrow.
[LUCY]
They're booked, boss!
Will this work?
Not in a hundred years!
That's practically
tomorrow at this rate!
For your consideration.
Not in ten years!
[LUCY]
Almost there!
Whaddaya think, boss?
I think it's time I
teach you to do layouts.
Awesome!
I meant it when I said
I wouldn't let you down.
And I've already been studying
about how to do
layouts on my own!
Cool as ice!
[LUCY] All the articles
have been edited, boss.
We've got a wicked
cool issue this week.
Thanks, rockstar.
And you've gotta be
excited about getting
your first one
published, huh?
[LUCY] Oh, yeah!
Tired, but super excited!
Thanks, I owe it all to you.
You did it yourself.
You don't owe me anything.
That's sweet.
[JASON]
Actually, you owe yourself.
One well-earned day off.
[gasps]
Cool.
It's already been a long night,
but I gotta do this.
[LUCY]
And that's how I wound up here.
[LUCY] All right,
I can handle the editing
and the layout no
problem, boss man!
You're a life-saver.
[LUCY gasps]
[JASON]
It's kind of a bummer.
This year's Grand Magic Games
aren't nearly as cool
as they used to be.
I mean, all of the guilds
that battled it out last year
were like totally
legendary, ya know?
Yeah, there definitely were some
truly great ones, weren't there?
There were.
Especially Fairy Tail.
Well, we're not really
a guild anymore, so--
You still have the
emblem on your hand.
But you guys did
kinda break up.
And you were so cool.
[LUCY] It's been almost a year
since I've been in contact
with any of my old friends.
I've been way too busy.
Yeah, right, who am I kidding?
[LUCY] I needed to give
everyone some space, is all.
They can't follow their own
paths with me tagging along.
That's not true either.
This sucks.
[LUCY] I was just too
scared to face them.
I miss Fairy Tail!
[NEIGHBOR A] Shut up, will ya?!
I'm trying to sleep!
Jeez, how embarrassing.
[LUCY]
The truth be told,
the main reason I became
a reporter in the first place
was to gather all the
information I could find.
From verified eyewitness
accounts to gossip.
All of it.
[LUCY] This whole year
has been one long search.
Still no solid leads
on Natsu and Happy.
It's like they just disappeared.
All I can think about
is finding them.
So we can be a family again.
[crying]
[LUCY]
But it's never gonna happen.
[LUCY] It's over, Lucy.
Fairy Tail's done.
Well. Okay.
It's time to get movin'!
[PLUE gibbers]
[LUCY]
Back to work.
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] Here it is folks,
the day of reckoning!
Who will take home
the coveted title
of "Fiore's Mightiest Guild"?
Let's find out!
I've got my predictions.
And how about you, sir?
I can't quite say.
Surely our old friend Mato
can provide some insight!
[MATO]
I'll try, punkin!
[CHAPATI]
Well, anyone who's been watching
could've seen this one coming.
Chrisark and Dullahan Head
have powered their way
into the finals!
Yo-ho!
[CHAPATI] They've got a
challenge on their hands
from the underdogs of
the Scarmiglione guild,
who have pulled off
one miraculous comeback
after another!
This year's games have
been a little different.
Since it's a single
elimination tournament,
both of these guilds
have remained undefeated
up to this very point, but
that's about to change for one!
Last round! It's on! So cool!
This has "feature story"
written all over it!
Maybe a special issue?
You there?
Huh? Say what?
I kinda zoned out.
It's cool. But it's showtime!
The final battle!
Oh yeah, it's gonna
be a blowout.
Have you been zoning
out this whole time?
Scarmiglione are like the kings
of "come from behind" victories.
There's so much drama.
Can they do it again?
Maybe. I think they might!
[LUCY]
Yup, that's exactly my point.
Chrisark is definitely tough.
It's true.
But according to everything
I've seen from them.
Scarmiglione's members have
gotta be tougher by a mile.
[JASON]
Huh?
I think every single one of them
has twice the magic power
that ol' Chrisark does.
They've just been hiding it.
Say what? That's crazy talk!
Why in the heck would
they wanna do that?
So they could gin up the odds
with all the bookies, obviously.
[JASON]
What?
Scarmiglion's gonna win.
There's no doubt about it.
Cool!
[CROWD cheering]
What an upset! I'm speechless!
Who'da thunk it? Not I.
[MATO]
Ooh, my.
[CHAPATI] Overcoming
incredible 100-to-1 odds,
Scarmiglione takes home the gold
in this year's
Grand Magic Games!
Worked like a charm.
[CHAPATI]
That's right, folks!
The only guild worthy of the
title "Fiore's Mightiest"
is Scarmiglione!
I can smell the money.
[JASON laughs]
You nailed it, Lucy.
They're best in the land.
I definitely never said that.
They may have won the games
this year, but still...
Who's that?
I have no idea.
[BOTH gasp]
Hold on a minute.
Somebody's entering the arena.
Who is it?
[YAJIMA]
Hm?
[MATO]
Huh?
[CHAPATI gasps]
[CHAPATI]
Ladies and gentlemen,
a mysterious individual has
walked onto the battlefield.
Who in the hell are you?
What's going on?
Something's weird.
So much magic power.
Everyone needs to
get out of here!
[SCARMIGLIONE B]
You've got guts friend,
but you're short on brains.
[SCARMIGLIONE C]
Wait, is this the "man in black"
people have been talking about?
[SCARMIGLIONE D]
Nah, there's no way.
So you clowns think you're
Fiore's greatest guild, do ya?
Huh?
All right, man, who are ya?
Who me?
[NATSU]
I'm a challenger!
[ALL screaming]
He unleashed a brutal attack!
We need to find some wizards
who can fight him off!
[WOMAN A]
This is horrible!
[MAN A]
t's so hot!
[MAN B]
Oww!
Hold on to your horses.
And your clothing.
The whole stadium is
melting like butter!
[gasping]
[LUCY]
This heat is frikkin' insane!
[chuckles]
This heat. Fire.
[gasps]
Natsu?
[JASON]
Cool!
It's Natsu Dragneel!
Holy smokes!
[MATO]
Punkin!
[HAPPY] Hey! It's been
a while. How ya doin'?
Happy!
You're back?
Yeah, well, Natsu
insisted on challenging
whoever won this year's
Grand Magic Games,
so here we are, I guess.
[LUCY] They don't seem to be
putting up much of a fight.
Whoever wants a piece,
come and get some!
[WIZARDS yelling]
[NATSU]
Now we're talkin'!
[WIZARDS screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[WIZARD A]
Take him down!
[WIZARDS yelling]
[chuckles]
[NATSU]
I'm all fired up now!
[WIZARDS gasping]
[WIZARD A]
The place is burning up!
[WIZARD B]
I feel like I'm on fire!
No! He's a monster!
[WIZARD E]
Run!
He's crazy.
But to his credit, he knows
how to make an entrance.
Hey! Good to see ya, Lucy!
How's it goin'?
[LUCY] At that moment,
I heard a voice inside my head.
Pretty good.
[LUCY] It said that Fairy Tail
is still alive and kickin'!
[HAPPY] Whoa, can you believe
we ran into Lucy like that?
[NATSU]
Has it really been a whole year?
[HAPPY] I gotta say, I'm in
shock Fairy Tail disbanded.
That's seriously messed up.
[NATSU] I can't imagine how
hard it must've been on Lucy.
[HAPPY]
I know.
Do ya think there's anything
we can do about it?
[NATSU]
Hmm.
I've got a great idea
that's sure to work!
[HAPPY]
I can always count on you!
[NATSU]
Aw, yeah! I'm fired up now!
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Next Time: "Message of Flame."
[NATSU]
Let's go, Happy!
Time to start a
brand new adventure!
[HAPPY]
Aye, sir!