What is she doing?
Her power's incredible!
[DIMARIA]
My ultimate spell.
Take Over God Soul.
[gasps]
The strength of a god?
You can unlock a source of
magic known as the Third Origin.
This technique will
allow you to access
all the power you have
the potential to gain
throughout your life.
But once you tap into that
power, it'll be gone forever.
You will never be able
to use magic again.
The ether-nano in your body will
be completely extinguished.
It cannot be regenerated.
I know it's a difficult
decision to make.
However, to stand any
chance of beating her,
this is the option you have.
If that's what it takes.
Okay!
[gasps]
I'd anticipated you would both
have strong reactions to this,
but there's a caveat.
I can only do this
for one of you,
the other must keep her
magic to heal Carla.
Make sure that she's okay.
That's your job.
I know! Which is exactly why
I have to fight for her now.
Let me!
I think it's why you need
to keep your magic.
So you can heal her and
fight together another day.
[WENDY]
But if you do this,
you'll never be able to
use magic ever again!
[SHELIA] Yeah, and it's the
same for you, you know!
I came out here today
because I wanted to help you!
If you lost your magic,
I would never forgive myself!
I'm ready to make
the sacrifice, Ultear!
And you're sure? This is
what you truly want?
If this is what it takes to save
my friends, then I'll do it.
Don't throw it away for me!
[DIMARIA]
What are you quarreling about?
[WENDY]
She's coming!
Come on, Ultear, I'm ready!
All right then. Here goes!
[WENDY yells]
I'll take care of her!
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Talon!
Hearken to my voice.
I am a god who has
control over time itself.
And time remembers all the
pain that's been inflicted
on your body over the years.
[screaming]
[DIMARIA]
Age Scratch!
[screaming continues]
[WENDY]
What's happening?
I've never felt pain like this!
Please don't do this.
You've gotta stop
before it's too late!
Before Wendy's used up
all of her magic power!
[WENDY] But if this is what
it takes to save my friends,
so be it!
You've made a grave mistake.
Do you not understand the folly
of a mortal trying
to touch a god?
[screaming]
[WENDY]
What's going on?
How can I already be
running out of strength?
[WENDY] Has my Third Origin
not been fully released yet?
Now pierce... to the
very end of time.
[WENDY]
I'm so weak.
But I gotta move!
[WENDY gasps]
[gasps]
Shelia?
[ULTEAR]
I made it... just in time.
I'll be handling
this one, Wendy.
There's no way I'm gonna lose.
Huh?
[SHELIA]
Sorry.
But we needed you to
buy us a little more time
while she used the Third
Origin spell on me.
Is that true?
Shelia and I both agreed
that this was for the best.
It was her idea?
You and I both know
Fairy Tail's battle
won't be over after this!
Which means Wendy is gonna need
all the power she can
get in the future!
So if there's still time,
I want you to use your
technique on me instead!
We're fighting a god, so we have
a better chance at winning
if you make me stronger!
All I want is for
everyone to survive this,
so please use the
Third Origin on me!
[WENDY]
No.
[SHELIA]
This'll be my final performance,
and I've never felt better.
Because I'm happy to
fight for my friends!
[DIMARIA grunts]
Hubris!
How dare you defy a god!
[SHELIA grunts]
[SHELIA] The only thing
I'm defying is evil!
But the fact that you're a god
is actually good for me,
because my power works best
against people like you.
It's God Slayer magic!
So that power is real?
I thought she was just bluffing!
She's losing grasp
over her God Soul!
Curse you!
But how?
I hit her with
everything I have.
An enchantment?
[SHELIA] I've screwed up
a lot of stuff in my life.
But there's one thing that
I've always been good at.
Magic.
Thanks to magic, I've met
so many wonderful people,
and gone on tons of adventures.
I love it so much,
and I know I always will.
Hang on, please.
[SHELIA] Even though
that will never change,
I'll have to go back
to an ordinary world,
where I'm just a regular person.
[SHELIA] This'll be the
last spell I'll ever use!
I swear to you!
I swear I'll always
be your friend!
And you'll be mine.
[yells]
[SHELIA] Everything I've
been through has taught me
what's really important
in this life.
[SHELIA]
Gathering Clouds of Heaven!
[DIMARIA screams]
[DIMARIA] My world...
is crumbling around me.
It's over.
No! Shelia!
[SHELIA]
Hurry. Help Carla.
[swords clanging]
[WENDY]
Time's moving again!
Carla!
I'm using my healing magic on
you, so you're gonna be okay!
[CARLA groans]
[coughing]
[CARLA]
Hm?
What's wrong?
Why in the world are you
crying this time, Wendy?
Because I feel bad.
It's all my fault.
I wanted to help Shelia.
That's the main reason I even
wanted to come here, but now--
Did I miss something?
Hold on a sec.
Where did Ultear go?
[SHELIA] It's okay,
Wendy. Please don't cry.
I'll be perfectly fine
living a normal life.
'Cause love is a whole
lot better than magic.
[ULTEAR]
Those girls, they're so strong.
If only I could've experienced
a love that powerful
when I was their tender age.
Poor guy.
It's okay. He'll wake
up before too long.
You're right.
Another Spriggan
Twelve's off the radar.
That's one more down!
Whoa! That means almost
half have been taken out!
That's awesome!
We got this, guys!
[ALL]
Yeah!
The eternal optimism
of the young.
[MAVIS gasps]
What's wrong? Is there
a problem, First Master?
The east.
The two remaining Spriggan
Twelve members aren't moving.
[MAKAROV]
Have they stopped their advance?
I have a strange
feeling about this.
[ALL]
Huh?
Wow, it's a nice guild
you got here.
[gasps]
[JACOB] Wood infused with
the fragrance of alcohol.
I'd heard this
was an old guild,
but it seems you've done
a spot of remodeling.
Hey! Who are you?
I'm one of the
distinguished members
of the Alvarez Empire's
Spriggan Twelve.
Name's Jacob Lessio,
if you're curious.
Oh, no!
But how? My radar says--
[gasps]
It was a good idea to
track us like that.
But you see, we have
this crafty old wizard
named August in our ranks.
He realized that our movements
were being watched,
so he had to go and fix
that, now didn't he?
You're seriously gonna
take us on all by yourself?
It's what I prefer.
Makes more sense for me.
No soldiers and nobody
else getting in my way.
Now don't get me wrong,
I do rather like
traveling with August,
the guy I mentioned earlier,
because he can really
hold his own, that one.
But I was feeling charitable,
so I came ahead of him.
Does your country honor
Respect for the Aged Day?
[JACOB] Judging from your
silence, that's a "no."
But back in Alakitasia,
that day is today.
A time when we can
let our elders know
that we cherish them and
everything they've done for us.
That's why I decided
I'd come here first
to get rid of you fairies.
And give old man August the
break that he so deserves.
[BOTH grunt]
Pour me a drink.
Make sure it's a strong one.
We're not giving a monster
like you a drop of alcohol.
Oh, well, that's a
real shame, innit?
I was gonna honor
you, too, old man.
I thought that sharing in the
very last drink of your life
might mean something.
[MAKAROV]
And this would be my last one?
[JACOB] You should know
I'm an assassin by trade.
Although I find it
unbecoming to brag,
my targets never meet me twice.
I've never heard of an assassin
who works out in
the open like this.
Perhaps there's no
one else like me.
Your typical assassin spends
hours lurking around,
hiding in shadowy places,
waiting for the
moment to strike.
But that's not the
way I do things.
Care to guess why?
Because I don't need to hide.
The bodies and witnesses
all disappear. That simple.
No one left to tell the tale.
So you make them all go away?
[FAIRY TAIL yelling]
What the hell is happening?!
This... can't be.
Makarov! Macao! Cana!
Where did everyone go?
Ah. One more left.
Seems we've got a
ghost on our hands.
[MAVIS]
That's strange.
Nobody outside of Fairy Tail
should be able to
see or hear me.
There you are.
[MAVIS screams]
[MAVIS]
I'm just a spirit!
How is he able to hurt me?
[JACOB]
Hey!
Are you just refusing
to talk to me, or what?
[MAVIS screaming]
I think I know who you are.
You're who the Emperor
was talking about.
The one he called Fairy Heart.
My guess is your body is
somewhere around here.
[MAVIS groans]
Talk.
[MAVIS gasps, screams]
[screaming]
Tell me where and I'll
bring back your friends.
I made them vanish
by putting them
in a place that's near death,
but not quite all the way there.
But if I decide to
leave 'em that way,
they'll be dead before long.
[MAVIS]
They're still alive.
So I want you to tell me
what to do with them.
[MAVIS]
If I choose my friends,
that means the world
could be doomed.
But I have no reason
to trust that this guy
will bring them back.
I don't know what to do!
Tell me!
Hee-ya!
[gasps]
[JACOB screams]
Hey, are you okay?
Did he hurt you?
[MAVIS]
Lucy! You're still here!
And so is Happy!
Aye, Sir! But, uh,
where is everyone?
He made them disappear
and he's going to kill them.
We have to stop him!
That must've been the
spatial magic from before.
You'd better let our
friends go, now!
Star Dress Change.
Time for Leo style!
What bollocks.
I cast that spell on
the entire guild hall,
so how'd I miss them?
[BOTH chuckle]
[FAIRY TAIL yelling]
[LUCY]
What is that?
Sounds like something crazy
is going on in there.
You think we should go
and check it out, or--?
[BOTH yelp]
[LUCY, HAPPY screaming]
It seems like I got here right
in the nick of time, Miss Lucy.
What are you doing here?
Well, you see,
I detected a major spatial
distortion just now.
"But hold on, why am I naked?"
you might ask embarrassedly.
Like it or not, it's simply
part of this defensive spell.
"It's too cramped
for three people!"
you might uncomfortably exclaim.
Hey, Natsu. That kinda tickles!
[HOROLOGIUM]
Miss Lucy.
Please try to remember that
you are a proper lady.
Well, once again, I owe ya one.
I won't be able to use this
defensive spell for a while,
so I ask that you
exercise caution.
[HAPPY]
Hm?
Hey, Lucy, check it out.
Fire Dragon--
Why did you make me look?
[MAVIS screaming]
[LUCY gasps]
Was that the First Master?
Let's go!
The stars were
lookin' out for us!
Aye, they were!
[chuckles]
[JACOB] Well, if you'd
vanished with the rest,
you would've avoided
what's about to happen.
Listen up, ghost. I'm changin'
the terms of the deal.
I think it'd be more fun to
tear this bird into pieces
until you've made up your mind.
[gasps]
[JACOB]
When the feeling strikes you,
I suggest you'd surrender.
Otherwise, she might just
be a pretty blonde head!
[MAVIS]
Lucy! Get out of the way!
[gasps]
[NATSU]
Even if she was just a head,
she'd still be our friend Lucy!
[gasps]
[NATSU] But since you
threatened her like that,
I'm gonna have to turn you
into a pile of ashes.
Natsu!
I knew he'd be okay!
I hope you had a nice nap.
Oh, yeah. Now I've got
a fire in my belly.
[NATSU]
Let's go!
[NATSU yells]
Flames, eh?
I'm fired up!
Hey, man, don't go
stealin' my line!
[JACOB groans]
And would you stop tearin'
up our damn guild hall?
What the--? He disappeared!
[HAPPY]
Uh-oh! Where'd he go?
[LUCY] Can you not even
smell him anywhere?
[NATSU sniffs]
[NATSU]
No! It's like he doesn't exist!
Here I am.
[growls]
[NATSU]
Uh! He's gone again? Damn it!
It's stealth magic.
He can make himself
completely invisible.
First Master!
But it's a bit more
than that, innit?
I can also see things
that are invisible.
Your friendly ghost,
for example.
[NATSU]
Don't you dare touch her!
He's not going anywhere.
He's just using a
camouflage spell!
Which means he's still here!
Loke!
[LOKE]
Lion Radiance!
Now what?
I see you!
This guy might be a problem.
[LOKE yells]
Loke!
That hurt. What'd you do?
[yells]
[screams]
Not good.
His weapon's invisible.
I hide and see all.
I send away and snuff out.
Those are the things
my magic can do.
Stop! You're hurting me!
[NATSU
Lucy!
You blocked because you thought
I was throwing something
at you, right?
I was actually crackin'
me whip behind me.
[MAVIS] This level of
power is what I'd expect
from one of Zeref's
Twelve shields.
Well, you can watch
me punch you!
Natsu!
If you wanna know
what hell's like,
I'd be happy to show
you firsthand.
[JACOB]
Now pay close attention
to the young lady
in front of you.
[LUCY gasps]
[gasps]
[grumbles]
Hey, wait!
What's going on? Why me?
[JACOB]
How do you like that?
I made her clothes invisible!
[NATSU]
Heh...?
[LUCY] Cut it out!
Turn them back to normal!
Uh, how about making
them invisible forever?
[LUCY]
Okay, I am closing your gate!
[JACOB] Now, this is
hell, don't you think?
Yeah, it is for me!
You've got a pretty weird
concept of hell, buddy.
[JACOB] What do you
mean by that, mate?
There's a half-naked girl
squirming in front of you!
Don't you feel tormented?
Embarrassed?
I mean, do you look away,
or not look away?
It has to be hellish!
I dunno, it's not like she
wears that much anyway.
[LUCY] I wear clothes
all the time, Natsu!
[JACOB] You're saying this
doesn't bother you
in the slightest?
[gasps]
[LUCY]
I'm a little bit confused here.
[JACOB grunts]
[LUCY]
What's wrong with your face?
It's obvious!
I mean, I can't just look
at you like that, can I?
This technique is something
like a double-edged sword,
because it puts me and
my target both through
an incredible amount
of anguish and torture!
[LUCY]
Uhh...
[snickers]
No, Lucy, please don't take your
underwear and stuff off, too!
Oh, no, don't make us
see your boobies!
No!
I think we should
play along with him!
Yeah, guess you're right.
My god! What kinda
sick people are you?
You'd really strip
in front of us!
[NATSU]
Whoa! Lucy, you're butt naked!
[LUCY]
Who cares? It's just skin!
I'm not afraid to
show off what I've got!
It's all so indecent!
[NATSU]
Holy crap! These are super soft!
[LUCY]
Oh, yeah! Don't stop, Natsu!
You're both so depraved
and terribly lewd!
[MAVIS]
That's it!
[JACOB] Enough! I'll just get
straight to the killin'!
[gasps]
Regulus...
Fire Dragon...
--[LUCY] ...Lucy Kick!
--[NATSU] ...Talon!
[HAPPY, NATSU laughs]
You brats.
You've made this
grown-up very angry!
[MAVIS]
I know what to do now!
How we can take down Zeref!
[LUCY]
In the middle of the guild hall,
we found a way to make the
assassin lose his focus.
But unfortunately,
that unleashes the full
force of his anger.
Changing tactics,
he decides to target
all the Fairy Tail
members trapped
in his weird,
alternate dimension.
Meanwhile, down in the south,
Hargeon is thrust
under a shadowy cloud
as a new enemy enters the fray.
Next Time:
"Historia of Corpses."
A dark threat looms
over the battlefield.