That can't be.
You're saying Zera's
just an illusion?
No. You're just trying to
play some kinda joke on me!
She's here! Zera's standing
right in front of us!
See? Right here.
Holding my hand.
It's only you and I here, Mavis.
What?
If you're in on this joke,
Zera, it's not very funny.
[ZERA]
Listen.
He's telling the truth, Mavis.
You've needed to know.
Seven years ago,
on Tenrou Island... I died.
I know you tried to save me,
but you were the only survivor.
Your feelings were so strong.
The magic energy inside
of you took on the form
of what you needed
most right then.
You needed a friend, so you
subconsciously created one.
Zera.
[ZERA]
Now when you create an illusion,
you're conscious of it.
You want others to see it and
react to whatever it may be,
but that wasn't the
case that night.
That's why no one
else can see me.
But look.
Since you're finally beginning
to think of me as an illusion,
I'm becoming more like one.
That's not true!
I would never think of you as
an illusion 'cause you're real!
Yuri only told you
because he wants you to
move on with your life.
[MAVIS gasps]
Me too. That's all we want.
But you can't if I'm still
around, so I have to go.
I'm sorry, Mavis.
No, please.
[ZERA] Keeping this
illusion going so long
has taken a toll on your health,
and your magic power.
Casting Law may've caused
your body to stop growing,
but it's not the only thing.
[MAVIS]
I don't care.
Even if no one else can
see you, I still can.
You're my best friend.
I love you.
I'm not ready to say goodbye
to you forever, Zera!
We had so many
good times together.
Are you seriously gonna read
all of those encyclopedias?
Of course I am!
Starting with "A."
That's where everything
begins, isn't it?
You can't go on a journey
without taking your first step!
[MAVIS]
Hey, Zera.
[ZERA]
Hm?
[MAVIS]
I wonder...
Where do you think we
could find a fairy?
I don't know.
Didn't your mom and dad tell
you something about them?
They said if I have faith
and keep searching,
I'll be sure to
find one someday.
Well then, that's what
I believe, too.
And I know you're not the kind
of person to give up her dream.
You really think I'll find one?
You will. Someday.
That's great! And I know
you'll be right there with me.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, we've been together
this long, haven't we?
So why not forever and ever?
[ZERA]
If you look in your heart,
maybe you'll find there's
already a fairy inside of it.
A fairy in my heart?
Oh, yeah. I'm sure of it.
I know this seems kinda silly...
Huh?
[MAVIS] But I was thinking.
Your hair looks like two tails.
Don't be mean!
I like this hairstyle!
[MAVIS laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[MAVIS] Ooh! Do you think
fairies have tails?
[ZERA]
Huh, I dunno.
[MAVIS]
No. I don't want this.
If you disappear on me,
I'll just have to use my
magic to create you again!
We can still be
together forever.
I know that's what you want.
But it only worked
the first time
because you weren't aware of it.
If you know I'm an illusion,
it can't be like before.
[MAVIS]
This can't be happening.
Please. Don't leave me, Zera.
You've always been there for me.
I'll be alone without you.
[ZERA]
You're not alone, silly.
You have real friends who
care so deeply for you.
It's time to be with them.
But I want you!
You promised that you'd stay
with me forever and ever!
You can't leave me!
[MAVIS crying]
Hey, Mavis. You know where you
can find a fairy, don't you?
[MAVIS]
Yeah. Inside my heart.
It's true. And I'll be there.
[ZERA]
I'm not leaving you.
I'll always be in
your heart. Forever.
Now, you gotta be brave.
And let me go there.
I wish I'd been nicer
to you in real life.
But the years I spent with
you were the best ever.
Thank you. They really were.
Promise me...
Promise me you'll
always be my friend.
Cross my heart.
[gasps]
Is that her?
Thank you for everything.
All I ask in return is that
you look after Mavis for me.
I will.
[ZERA]
Look after Mavis for me.
Do you hear that?
[PRECHT]
Zera.
Mavis was the only one
who could see or hear her.
It's so weird.
Yuri had said he wanted
to talk to her about Zera.
[PRECHT]
Was she real all along?
He told me only Mavis could
perceive her,
because she came from
her subconscious mind.
An illusion, but not.
Do you think that voice
we just heard was Zera?
Maybe if Mavis finally
realized what she was,
we could hear her, too.
Are you okay?
[MAVIS] Zera will still be a
part of me, like she always has.
She'll go on living in my heart.
So let's move on.
All of us together.
[MAVIS] When I started my
adventure, I had nothing.
Zero.
But now, I have Zera.
I'm so thankful for
everything she's done for me.
[PRECHT] Well, do you know
where Mavis is now?
I left her there.
What?
Zera asked you to look after her
and you're already
slackin' on the job?
That whole thing was
pretty heavy emotionally,
so I figured she'd
need some time alone
to sort out her feelings.
Guess that makes sense.
It's gotta be painful.
She was real to Mavis.
They spent all those
years alone together,
and then all of a sudden
she had to say goodbye.
Mavis told me that she wants
to go and look for fairies.
It sounds crazy. And I have
no clue where to look.
But still, I wanna
help her find them.
Me too.
If Mavis needs a
friend beside her,
I'd be more than honored to go.
[PRECHT]
Agreed.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[MAN A]
Blue Skull is finally gone!
[MAN B] Isn't it amazing?
We're free again!
[MAN C] No more of those jerks
tellin' us what to do!
[MAN D] Magnolia will be even
better than it was before!
It'll be awesome!
[MAN E] Everyone that that had
to run can come back home!
[BOY A]
I'm sorry!
[BOY B]
Thanks, Mom and Dad!
[GIRL A]
Yummy!
Well, Zera. What now?
What kind of adventure will I go
on in my next chapter of life?
Maybe I should try being a
treasure hunter with the boys
for a little while.
That could be exciting.
Or should I go home?
I could spend some more time
back on Tenrou Island
and see where I go from there.
I guess.... I just
gotta think about it.
I'm not exactly sure
that treasure hunting
is the perfect life for me.
[MAKO]
Miss Mavis!
Here's to the free
city of Magnolia!
[TOWNSPEOPLE]
Hear, hear!
[TOWNSPEOPLE laughing]
Do you want some bread?
We made it just for you!
You've done so
much for our city,
the least we can do
is make you dinner.
I just saw an opportunity
to help the people here
get things started is all.
And then you guys
took over from there.
You drove Blue
Skull out of town.
Come on!
If it wasn't for you
and your friends,
we'd still be under
Blue Skull's thumb.
You brought life
back to the city
and we're eternally
grateful for it!
I wish your friends
were here now,
so we could thank
them personally.
But still,
you can't help but wonder
what's next for Magnolia.
Aw, shut up!
Ya think this is really the time
for more doom and gloom?
Are you worried about
something in particular?
No, no. It's nothing, really.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, we came here to celebrate
our new freedom, right?
Don't get the wrong idea.
Blue Skull being gone is the
best thing that's happened here.
That was long overdue.
I suppose in some way
they had just become
like the devil you know.
Now that they're gone,
nobody really knows
what will happen next.
We'll be fine.
We'll figure things
out, I'm sure!
Tonight, let's forget
about all our worries!
[MAVIS]
Please excuse me.
I appreciate your hospitality,
but there's something
urgent that I need to do!
Don't go. Stay
and finish dinner!
Sorry. Some other time, promise!
Oh, but can I take
the bread with me?
I know it'll be yummy!
[KERSEY]
Uhh...
[MAVIS] I figured it out, Zera!
I know what I'm gonna do next!
Hey, there. It's good
to see ya, Mavis!
[PRECHT, WARROD]
Uhh...
[YURI clears throat]
So I think that's the way we
should greet her. With smiles.
We just wanna be super
cheerful, ya know?
Like this?
I'm so happy you're back, Mavis!
That's it!
Now hit me with a
million-Jewel smile!
[grunts]
[PRECHT]
Okay. Got it.
Hey there, Mavis!
Good to see you!
[YURI] You'll scare the
crap outta her with that!
Here she is! Are you guys ready?
Course I am!
[giggles]
[ALL]
Hey, there! Good to see you!
I've got a great idea!
So listen up!
[ALL] You think we should
start our own wizard guild?
Yep!
But, uh, we're already in
a treasure hunter guild.
[PRECHT]
We've dabbled a bit in magic,
but that doesn't quite make
us full-fledged wizards.
I thought you were going off
on an adventure to find fairies.
I plan on going on lots
of adventures, but still,
everybody needs a place
they can call home, right?
[MAVIS] That's why I'm
gonna start the guild
right here in Magnolia!
You don't wanna start
it on Tenrou Island?
Well, I did consider
that for a little while.
But then I thought about
all the people here
who'd lived under
Blue Skull for so long.
Their freedom is certainly
cause for celebration,
but everyone's anxious about
what will happen next.
[PRECHT]
Good point.
Blue Skull was oppressive,
but they did create
some kind of order,
and a certain fragile stability.
They're gone now, but they
left a big power vacuum.
What's gonna take their place
in the future, ya know?
Yes, exactly. Guilds are the
heart of cities like this one.
They need them to
grow and prosper.
Zera dreamed of
saving this city.
But it doesn't end with
kicking out Blue Skull,
and then going on our merry way.
We want the people here
to love life again.
To smile. To actually feel free.
To give them hope that tomorrow
will be better than yesterday.
If we put our heads together, we
can make that dream come true.
Since I'm from Tenrou,
we can declare the island as
the guild's "sacred ground."
Umm. Do you guys wanna join me?
[YURI]
Sounds like an adventure.
[WARROD]
Our own wizard guild.
[PRECHT] Might I suggest we call
ourselves the "Precht Brothers"?
[YURI] Can't believe you said
that with a straight face.
[PRECHT]
I'm being completely serious.
[YURI] Well, that name
seriously sucks.
[MAVIS]
I have a name.
We're going to call ourselves:
The Fairy Tail guild.
[GUYS]
Uh...
Are you sure about that?
That's kinda quirky.
Do you mean like
the tail of a fairy?
[PRECHT]
I don't get it.
What do Fairies have to
do with the three of us?
Do fairies have tails?
Or not? I don't really know.
More than that,
are fairies even real?
It's an eternal mystery,
and trying to find out sounds
like an eternal adventure to me.
Anyway, that's how
I came up with it.
Fairy Tail.
Starting a guild from
zero will be tough.
We have a lotta
work ahead of us.
I know we do.
That's why we need the people
of Magnolia behind us
every step of the way.
We can't do it without them.
So you wanna start a new
wizard guild in Magnolia?
The idea seems okay
in theory, but--
I don't know about all of this.
Word on the street
is that you people
haven't even been
wizards for very long.
Yes, that is true.
But we want to grow
in our abilities
and have the city grow
right along with us.
We don't wanna cause trouble.
All we really want is for
our guild to spread joy
to everybody that lives here.
I truly believe that
if we work together
with the people of Magnolia,
there's nothing
we can't achieve.
We can be a beacon of hope
for the whole kingdom.
You can count me in!
If there's anybody that
can make an amazing guild,
it's gotta be you guys!
You're gonna be the
best guild ever!
You have my blessing, Mavis!
I'd be proud to have you here!
This might be good.
And we definitely can't
afford another situation
like what happened
with Blue Skull.
We've all seen that you care.
You've already saved
Magnolia once
from the brink of destruction.
Yeah, but if they go overboard
with their magic spells,
they could break a whole
lotta buildings and stuff
all over again.
You'll be careful
and not let things get too
outta hand, won't ya?!
Don't you worry!
We'll make sure that nothing
like that will ever happen!
[KERSEY] Okay. If you
promise, I believe ya.
[CROWD laughing]
[MAVIS] After that, we
petitioned the Magic Council
to allow us to establish
a new guild in Magnolia.
We also joined the community
of neighboring guilds
and the regional
guild federation.
The next step was for
Yuri and the others
to officially leave
Sylph Labyrinth
so they could found
Fairy Tail with me.
So if you ever find
yourself in Magnolia,
feel free to drop in and see us.
Hey, Sword, Hammer, and
Sniper. See ya later!
Yeah! I totally wish
you guys good luck!
Maybe we'll get a chance to work
together some day. Ya dig?
Don't get too far outta range!
[SWORD sighs]
[SWORD]
Well, there they go.
And I totally couldn't be
happier to see them leave.
[HAMMER]
Mh-hm.
No matter what those
guys are doing,
they just can't seem
to stay outta trouble.
When I heard they were
takin' on Blue Skull,
I really thought it was
game over for 'em.
[HAMMER]
Mh-hm!
[SWORD]
Hm.
All right, fellas,
if you think those losers
are gonna start an awesome guild
and totally not regret the day
they left Sylph Labyrinth,
raise your hand!
[SYLPH LABYRINTH chattering]
If you think they're gonna
totally screw it up,
raise your hand!
[SYLPH LABYRINTH cheers]
Still, if I know
those three guys,
no matter what might
happen to 'em,
they'll totally have
fun wherever they go.
[MAVIS] Time went on,
then one day...
[MAVIS] Hey, Warrod!
Get over here, will ya? Hurry!
Hey. There he is!
[PRECHT]
He does like to take his time.
You were off
day-dreamin,' weren'tcha?
Take a look. There's
one dream come true.
Whoa. Amazing.
It's our very own guild.
[YURI]
Sure is.
[MAVIS] Let's take a picture
so we never forget this!
The day that Fairy
Tail was born!
So, Master, somethin'
you'd like to say?
Uh, did you say "Master"?
Well, startin' the guild
was your idea, wasn't it?
I don't really have much
to say about fairies.
Okay.
[clears throat]
My wish is for this
guild to be a family
that loves and cherishes
each one of our members.
And I believe that "comrade"
is more than just a word.
A comrade lives in your heart.
Is someone you can
trust unconditionally.
I want you to feel like
you can rely on me.
Because one day, I'll need you.
And our trust in each
other will see us through.
Whenever you're suffering,
whenever you're sad,
I'll be there to make
sure you remember
that you never have
to face it alone.
We have as many hopes and dreams
as there are stars in the sky.
If we walk toward
the future together,
I know we'll reach them.
Now, let us move forward.
Forever in tune with
the song of the fairies.
[GEOFFREY]
Fairy Tail, hmm?
In that case, I'll have to
start a new guild of my own
to exact my revenge.
A guild of dark souls.
And I will be the Phantom Lord.
[MAVIS]
Zera.
When I look into the future,
I see many people gathering
around this guild.
Together, as a family.
And they all have
a place to return to
on this eternal adventure.
I know in my heart that someday,
my dream for Fairy
Tail will come true.
[NARRATOR] On that bright
April day in the year 686,
the Fairy Tail guild
is officially founded.
Its first master
is Mavis Vermillion.
In July of that same year, the
bloody Second Trade War begins.
In February, 688, Fairy Tail
and Fiore's other Wizard guilds
intervene in the war.
Mavis's expertise in strategy
earns her the name
"Fairy Tactician"
throughout the kingdom.
Two years later, in May of 690,
Yuri Dreyar finds
a girl he treasures
and the pair is soon married.
Shortly after that,
the Second Trade War
finally comes to an end
and the Inter-Guild Conflict
Ban Treaty is established.
In March of 696,
Yuri's son, Makarov, is born.
The next year,
Mavis passes away,
and her grave is built on the
sacred ground of Tenrou Island.
Per Mavis' wishes,
Precht becomes her successor
and Fairy Tail's second master.
Then, in 700, Yuri Dreyar
joins Mavis in the afterlife.
731, Precht becomes involved
with black sorcery.
Shortly thereafter, Warrod
Sequen leaves the guild.
In 736, Precht leaves
the guild as well
and appoints Makarov Dreyar
to be the guild's third master.
Much later, in 784, primary
guild members go missing
after Acnologia attacks
Tenrou Island.
Following that loss, in 785,
Macao Conbolt becomes
the fourth master.
In 791, the Tenrou Team
returns after seven years.
Gildarts Clive becomes
the fifth master.
Once again, Makarov Dreyar
becomes the sixth master.
He leads the guild to victory
in the Grand Magic Games.
Okay! Let our eternal
adventure begin!
[GUYS]
Yeah!
[ZERA chuckles]
[ZERA]
Good luck, Fairy Tail!
[MAVIS] So this is the story
of Fairy Tail's creation.
My dream really did come true.
And Fairy Tail became a guild
that's more like a family,
where each member is
loved and cherished.
Unfortunately, I was wrong about
the guild never causing trouble.
They seem to have a hard
time staying out of it.
The property damage bills have
been too numerous to count.
Sadly, Fairy Tail is
currently disbanded.
But as long as everyone
still has the spirit
that we founded the guild upon,
love, trust, and friendship,
and they keep the guild
in their hearts,
I have faith that they'll
all find each other
and re-form stronger
than ever before.
I believe in you, Fairy Tail!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's going to be a
thrilling day four
of the 792 Grand Magic Games!
The first match up of the day
is about to get started,
and you do not wanna miss it!
[chuckles]
[LUCY] It's been a full year
since Fairy Tail was disbanded.
All of our members have
gone our separate ways,
seeking new adventures.
I've been working as
an apprentice reporter
for Sorcerer Weekly,
and my job is to cover
all the action
in this year's
Grand Magic Games.
Little did I know that
I was about to have
a fateful encounter.
In 792, the newly rebuilt
royal capital of Crocus
burns once again.
Next Time: "Challenger."
Unbroken, the emblem
burns even brighter.