It's Laxus.
I never thought
I'd be this happy to see him.
Isn't he the
master's grandson?
[HADES]
I see.
So you're a blood
relative of Makarov.
♪
[LAXUS]
How pathetic.
You guys got beat
so bad you look like
a bunch of tattered rags.
No joke!
[ERZA]
What are you doing here, Laxus?
[LAXUS] I came
to pay my respects to
the first guild master.
I used to be a member
of Fairy Tail too, y'know.
I was just planning
to stop by Mavis' grave,
so this is a big surprise.
I certainly didn't expect to run
into the second guild master.
I've got an idea,
since you're already here,
how about I dig
a grave for you, too?
[HAPPY]
The Man Without an Emblem!
[HADES]
My.
What a shame.
To think that poor Makarov
would be burdened by such
a pretentious grandson.
Good.
I'm impressed with
your magic power.
Not to mention your courage.
I didn't realize the
boy had more than one pawn
of Gildarts' caliber.
[LAXUS] You know, that
reminds me of something
the geezer used to say.
"Whenever you face a tough
enemy it doesn't matter
how strong they are.
Standing up to them
is what's most important."
Ain't that right.
Natsu?
[NATSU]
Yeah, you bet.
Utter nonsense.
That's nothing more than
a weakling's excuse.
Think you're
strong enough to face me?
Then let's see what you've got!
[LAXUS]
If you insist.
Defense Enchantments can't have
even the tiniest of holes,
or they'll be rendered useless.
So double-check every detail.
It's my turn
to protect you now.
Ya big lug.
If you have something
to confess, then speak up.
It's not like
that and you know it!
There you go.
You should lie down for a bit.
You need your rest.
[ELFMAN] Nah, I'm
through with lyin' down.
Let me help you keep watch.
While you were out.
you kept talking in your sleep.
"Evergreen!
Evergreen!".
Weird, huh?
It's not
what you're thinkin'!
[LISANNA]
I'm just kidding!
You're so silly
[BIXLOW] Aw C'mon, would you
guys please get serious?
[TOMMENS]
Yeah, get serious!
You're one to talk!
Where've you been, slacker?
[BIXLOW] Getting rid of that guy
with the glasses we knocked out.
We can't risk him
using a Body Link spell
and giving away our location.
Good work, Bixlow.
We're just wrapping
things up here.
[LEVY] You two should get some
rest while you have the chance.
You must be exhausted.
[BIXLOW] After dealing
with the guys who barged
into enemy territory
this is a piece o' cake!
[YOMAZU]
Pierce!
Bixlow-?
No way!
That's Eastern Solid Script!
[LEVY]
Not him again!
Heavy Egg Rain!
It's an ambush!
[FRIED] They must've traced
our whereabouts somehow!!
[LEVY] I thought Gajeel
beat these guys earlier!
I Guess not!
[YOMAZU]
Surprise!
Screw battle etiquette!
It means nothing to a warrior
who's lost his blade!
Zubabababa!
The Enchantment!
Protect the injured!
Please let me fight, too!
No, you can't-
If we don't beat you down,
Master Hades is gonna be angry.
Real angry.
We won't let him down!
Besides, thanks to the bedlam
you've caused our guild.
We'll be promoted
to the Seven Kin of Purgatory
once we get rid of you
and your friends!
No way!
Wait!
We have to restore
the Enchantment first!
But, Fried!
Get up, Bixlow!
Take them out!
[BIXLOW]
You got it.
Just leave 'em to me!
Let's go.
babies!
[TOMMENS]
Go!
Sayth Magic?
Well in that case!
Boh!
[KAIN]
Ow!
Cut it out!
That hurts!
[LISANNA]
What's with him?
He's tough!
Well duh, of course I am.
I've reinforced myself.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Didn't Happy steal
that doll from you?
[KAIN] I always carry
a spare just in case.
I call him Mr. Cursy the Second.
[LISANNA]
"The Second"?
Being the
skilled warrior I am,
I've already managed to
get my hands on one of
your pretty, white hairs, yeah.
You jerk!
[KAIN]
You ain't seen nothin' yet!
As much as I hate being
defeated, I'll admit that
it taught me a thing or two.
Okay, Cursy the Second,
turn into iron!
Listen, hot stuff.
If you wanna get back together
with me, just say so.
What's with you?
You're not makin' sense!
Then you
leave me no choice.
I learned this from
the last guy who defeated me!
Metallic Rocket the Second!
[ELFMAN]
Wha-?
Big Brother Elf?
[ELFMAN]
Look out, Lisanna!
[KAIN] Isn't sibling love
a remarkable thing?
Lots of girls tell me
"I wish I was your sister!"
But I know they're just
looking for an excuse
to get close to me.
Ouch!
Bet that hurt!
But ya shouldn't mess
with one of the Seven Kin!
Now, you might be small
fries but that's not gonna
stop me from destroying you!
We won't lose.
We refuse to!
We'll keep fighting.
Because we're Fairy Tail!
[MACAO]
What's the hold up?
Why hasn't Romeo made it
back to the guild yet?
Alzack and Bisca
let him tag along on a job.
What?
They probably ditched him
somewhere so they go make out,
knowing those two.
Those two makin' out?
Yeah, right!
Get real!
So, is it just me.
Or do we have
a lot of new members?
Yep.
And that's a good thing.
We need a bunch more folks
to handle all these requests
we've been getting.
Yeah, no joke!
Just look at all these fliers!
Why do you
sound so excited?
You never go on any jobs.
Check it out, guys.
I've finished
my latest routine!
I call it.
the "Supreme Dance"!
Way to go.
Dance your heart out.
Whoa, Droy!
If you don't stop eating
you're gonna blimp out!
Nah, it's fine!
I eat a lot but
I never gain weight!
Laki!
Long time, no see!
Yeah, I've had a lot
of long-term jobs lately.
I'd stop
binging if I were you.
Unless you wanna
look like Reedus here.
Oui.
But the only reason I'm this
big is because of my magic.
Hey Dad, I'm back!
Good!
About time!
Geez!
I can't even keep track
of how many jobs you've been
tagging along on lately.
Well, What do you expect?
He is the son of a wizard.
It's sad to see that
his dad's not the one
he looks up to, though.
Get off my case!
Aw, man.
It's boring around here
without Natsu and the gang.
You wanna be just like
Natsu when you grow up, dontcha?
No matter how
many members we gain,
it always seems
so quiet when they're gone.
Yeah, you can say that again.
We're without our best
team the S-Class wizards.
and the Dragon Slayers.
We're still the strongest
guild in Fiore but right now
we're missing our main forces.
No wonder it's quiet.
[NAB]
S-Class, huh?
Do you think they might have
a job only I could pull off?
I'd like to find something
that really suits me.
Maybe you should
just try one of the jobs
in front of you first!
It's time to quit
staring at the board
and just pick one already!
Okaaay!
[ROMEO] I can't believe
the S-Class trial
is happening right now!
I wonder how it's going.
[WAKABA] We've got another set
of good contenders this year!
Which reminds me.
why did Wendy
go along with them?
She was someone's
partner, wasn't she?
No, wait.
That's not right.
Did master choose
seven candidates?
Wow, you guys are getting old!
You've already forgotten
who's competing this year?
Hey Dad.
You think Natsu'll win?
I can't wait
for the next trial!
'Cause I'm gonna be
an S-Class wizard for sure!
[MACAO]
Hold your horses, kiddo.
You've gotta become
a regular wizard first.
[ROMEO]
Oh, I will!
I'm all fired up!
I'm afraid that
searching as a group
isn't going to get us anywhere.
I think it would
be best to split up.
[HAPPY]
Good idea!
You're as smart
as you are pretty!
By "split up".
Do you mean each
of us search alone?
[HAPPY]
Are you scared?
[PANTHERLILY]
Absolutely not!
Let's split up!
[HAPPY]
Alright!
I'm sorry!
[HAPPY]
Uhhhh!
Maybe in here?
Geez!
What kind of
freaky ship is this?
I am not afraid.
Not at all.
This one looks suspicious.
No luck.
So much for splitting up.
It was worth a shot.
I Guess we might as well
continue searching as a group.
Sure.
That's fine with me.
Not too shabby.
You guys really know how
to put up a fight, dontcha?
Mess with Grimoire
Heart and you'll find yourself
in a world of pain, bok-kah!
It's time
to finish you off!
Prepare to die!
Who did that?
[CANA] I've had
enough of you guys.
You've disrupted the trial.
You've hurt my friends, and now
you're attacking the injured.
If anyone's gonna find
themselves in a "world of pain"
it'll be you two!
[FRIED]
Hurry to Lisanna's side.
Hold on,
what about the Enchantment?
[FRIED] I've already enabled
its minimum level of defense.
Right now getting rid of
these scoundrels should be
our number one priority.
You ready?
You know it!
[FRIED]
Ah, so that's it.
They worked together
to attack Gahjeel.
I wondered how such inferior
wizards could defeat him.
[BIXLOW] Neither of these
clowns could've pulled it off
in a one on one fight!
Hang in there, Bro!
You gotta stay strong!
I'm tryin'.
Now listen up.
There's only one way
you're ever gonna be able
to beat these jerks.
and that's with a
coordinated team attack.
You've just gotta
trust me on this one.
They're too strong for you alone
but you can take 'em as a team!
I really wish
I could walk right now.
Oh crap!
Is that an
Amaterasu Spell?
Now die!
What the hell?
[HADES] Those hit by the
Amaterasu Formula lose
all strength in their limbs
and become immobilized.
Simply blocking it
consumes so much magic power
it can be fatal.
He's awesome!
[ERZA] I had no idea
Laxus was this powerful.
[LAXUS] To think,
that was only one leg.
I still have the other one
and both my hands.
Not to mention
the rest of me.
If I combined 'em
into one attack.
it'd be a hell of a lot
stronger than the kick that
just took you down.
You wanna try me?
[HADES]
You talk big.
Although I can't blame you.
There's an air of confidence
that comes with youth.
but it's not
indicative of your skill.
You can't beat me!
Just watch me!
[KAIN]
I've got you now.
You're in a
sorry state, aren't ya?
Well, that's what you get
for trying to seduce
a pure heart like mine.
What?
I wasn't trying to seduce you!
Now then.
I think it's about time
for me to finish you off.
I promise I'll do my
best to make it quick so
you don't have to suffer-
[LISANNA]
Cana!
[KAIN]
Hot!
Why did you burn
my bristles, lady?
To teach you
a lesson, fatty!
You need to drop
that cocky attitude!
I'm not a fatty,
I'm just big-boned!
[CANA]
Card Magic.
Summoned Lightning!
[KAIN]
That tingles.
[CANA]
What the-?
[KAIN] You're overwhelmed by
my manliness, aren't ya?
Y'know, I don't have a "type" so
I'm an equal opportunity lover.
I never turn a lady down.
Does that surprise you?
[CANA]
No.
I'm surprised my
attack's not affecting you.
That's 'Cause Cursy
the Second is a generator!
Self-Reinforcement.
Lightning Bolt!
Why don't
you bolt outta here!
Nice try!
But your attack was easily
dodged by changing the-Whoa,
that's cold!
You need a cold shower!
No!
When cotton absorbs water.
it gets heavy!
[CANA] I'm not
finished with you yet!
Icicles!
[KAIN]
Self-reinforcement.
Heat!
[LISANNA]
Cana's amazing!
She's holding her own
against this guy!
I think she could win
the S-Class trial this year!
It's been quite a while
since I had two beautiful women
fight over me like this.
It's kinda like
high school all over again.
I'm flattered, ladies.
[CANA] So Are you trying
to distract us or are you
just that clueless?
Is this guy
bothering you?
He was.
Let's all
take him out together!
[KAIN] Wait a sec,
lemme get this straight.
If I heard right you lovely
ladies all wanna go out
on a date with me?
A confession of love
from three beauties at once?
This isn't anything
like high school at all!
I'm the maaan!
Now Listen up!
I'm not a flirt, okay?
I'm an old-fashioned gentleman!
I hate to say this
but I can only go steady
with one of you!
So Will the lady who
really wants to date me
please step forward?
[ALL THREE]
Don't look at me.
I'm crying tears of joy!
Everybody knows that I'm single
and lovin' every minute of it!
Solid Script: Hole!
[CANA]
Explosive Flame!
[LISANNA]
Penguin!
[KAIN]
Heavy!
Oh no!
Lisanna!
Hey!
Look down!
How'd he
turn into my brother?
[ELFMAN]
Ow.
You're So heavy.
[KAIN]
Did you like that?
I call it
Self-Reinforcement Overlap!
a taboo technique
using Cursy the Third!
By attaching both mine
and the big lug's bristle,
I can switch bodies with
him whenever I want!
You're screwed now
that I've self-reinforced
into a mist!
It'll be even more
frustrating than trying
to attack a big, fluffy,
thunder cloud in the sky.
What the.
You tricked me!
Where'd that come from?
Well, Fried had a
feeling that this might happen.
So he went ahead and set up
a few of 'em before
the fighting got started.
This Enchantment
trap keeps wizards
from using their magic!
[CANA]
Nice!
[KAIN]
Lemme out.
We can overlap
techniques too, y'know!
Let's do it!
Lisanna!
[LISANNA]
Ready!
Flames in my right
hand and storms in my left!
Triple Unison.
Explosion!
No!
I got beat by a girl again!
Where's the fun in that?
Bahk.
Somethin' tells me he lost.
Yeah.
good news for us.
Our chances at a
promotion just skyrocketed,
bok-kah!
Those losers are happy
their buddy got beat down?
That's how
it works in a dark guild.
I doubt we'd ever
be able to understand.
[BIXLOW]
Only two left.
[FRIED] Let's make
quick work of them.
[BIXLOW]
Right on!
[HADES] Well, would you
look what we have here?
I knew you were full of bravado
but I didn't expect you to fall
to your knees so soon.
Laxus!
Come on.
Please get up!
[LUCY] He was hit by
that spell after all!
[LAXUS] I've traveled
almost everywhere,
all over this world of ours.
But this is the
first time I've ever met
such a monster.
I've got a long way to go.
What're you saying?
You've gotta pull
yourself together, man!
[HADES] I'm glad I could help
you come to that realization.
"Laxus" was it?
But this is the end.
Prepare to die!
Hurry and get up!
[LAXUS]
I realize.
I'm not a member
of Fairy Tail anymore.
Look out!
Move or it's gonna hit you!
[GRAY]
Laxus!
[LAXUS] But this bastard
took out my grandpa.
So I'm allowed
to take revenge, right?
Yeah, of course you are!
[NATSU]
Lightning?
Laxus!
[LAXUS]
This one's my treat.
Natsu.
What's happening to him?
[NATSU]
Hey.
Thanks for the meal.
[HADES]
An electric charge?
[LAXUS]
I gave him all my magic power.
He what?
He transferred
his power to Natsu!
[GRAY]
Are You kiddin' me?
Does that
mean he ate lightning?
If he eats anything other
than fire it makes him sick!
[GRAY] But if that's the
case then Laxus didn't have
any magic power left
when he was hit!
[WENDY] He was willing to risk
his life in order to help us.
[NATSU] Why did
you give it to me?
You know that
I'm weaker than you.
[LAXUS] It has nothin' to do
with who's weaker or stronger.
He wounded Fairy Tail's master.
It's only right
that someone with
the guild's emblem
take him down!
Anyone who hurts
the guild deserves
what's comin' to 'em!
So go get him, Natsu.
[NATSU]
Okay!
It's a fusion
of flame and lightning.
[WENDY]
A lightning flame dragon!
[NATSU] You're gonna pay
for what you've done.
♪
[HAPPY]
"Lightning Flame Dragon"?
Showing off much?
[NATSU]
No!
I mean, it's not like
I'm trying to or anything.
[HAPPY] If you were a real
pal you would've shared
some of Laxus' power with me!
[NATSU]
Whatever!
Even if I had, you'd still be
nothin' more than a flyin'
"lightning cat".
[HAPPY]
Yeah, right!
That's what you think!
I'd be a thunder cat!
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next time: Realm of the Abyss!
[HAPPY] Lily's scared of
thunder, so that would keep him
far away from me!
And then he couldn't
copy me anymore!
[NATSU] You think
Lily's copying you?
Keep dreamin'!