[NARRATOR]
On an otherwise pleasant day,
an egg suddenly
plummeted out of the sky
and into the midst
of our heroes.
Natsu and Happy
cared for the egg,
naming the strange creature that
hatched from it, "Kemo-Kemo."
They treated the little tike
as a member of their family.
Shortly after,
a Council-initiated
wizard exchange program began.
Each of the top six guilds
from the Grand Magic Games
was invited to participate.
Natsu took this
opportunity to ask
the members of the other
guilds if they knew anything
about Kemo-Kemo, but his
efforts were to no avail.
Not even the wisest among them
had seen such a creature.
Upon arriving at the
Sabertooth Guild-hall,
Fairy Tail's group learned
the exchange program
had been cancelled due
to the abrupt appearance
of a strange island.
The Magic Council requested
that the guilds join forces
to investigate. However...
The Magic Council has
ordered me to tell you this.
"The island is dangerous." So...
That's it?
[LUCY gasps]
[WENDY] There! All finished.
Feeling better yet?
[NATSU sighs]
Yeah, thanks.
So. Anything else
you can tell us?
We do know this:
there's some being on
that island that's alive.
I keep my phrasing vague
because of the nature
of the signal we detected.
Human or animal, it was
too strange to identify.
Well, thanks for tellin' us
before we agreed to come along.
So then that's what
we'll be looking for?
[LAHAR] Hm. I'll be
watching from the coast
while you commence
your investigation.
Should you need support
or reinforcement,
launch a flare.
[ERZA]
I understand.
[HAPPY]
The Place You Came To!
[NATSU]
That's weird.
How does a newly formed
island get footpaths?
[LUCY] Maybe people used
to live here a long time ago.
Like, before the island
sunk in the first place.
An island sinkin'
I can understand,
but why would it pop back up?
It's so weird.
But I bet those ruins would
be a good place to find out.
They look all dark and scary,
like they're haunted.
Ya know, I think
it may be haunted.
[ERZA] Let's split up and
investigate the area.
We'll rendezvous at the
ruins and go in together.
[NATSU] Well this is lame.
It's just a dumb forest.
[HAPPY] I'm gettin' pretty
hungry. When's our lunch break?
[CARLA] Please try to take
this assignment seriously.
[gasps] Hey! Come and
check this out!
[NATSU, ERZA, LUCY]
Hm?
Whoa! Seems like this island
really was underwater.
[NATSU gasps] Those shells
look kinda familiar, too.
[ERZA]
Hm. I remember them as well.
From the back of the
stone tablet at Lamia Scale.
[HAPPY]
Woo-hoo!
[LUCY, ERZA gasp]
Forget those shells.
We've hit the jackpot!
[ERZA]
Deep sea fish?
Like the ones from Mermaid Heel.
Come, my lunch.
You smell so exotic!
The word you're searching
for is "rancid!"
I bet a bunch of stuff
from beneath the sea
got dragged up with
the island, but...
Somethin' still doesn't add up?
It's like Rogue said, there's
a full-grown forest here.
If the island were underwater
until a few days ago, then...
...that shouldn't be possible!
[NATSU]
Hm.
You're right.
This place makes
no sense, yet here it is.
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[ALL yelp]
The heck is that?
[MONSTER 224A roars]
We found our target.
The ruins, let's go!
[ROGUE]
Right!
[ALL gasp]
[ERZA] The council couldn't
tell that thing from a human?
[roars]
[GRAY]
They must be idiots!
[STING] Hey, Natsu!
That thing's a sea serpent!
[NATSU]
Never heard'a one.
[STING] No? Well, it's
about what it sounds like.
Looks like a serpent.
Lives in the sea.
Then why is it not
there right now?
[roars]
[ALL yelp]
[NATSU, LUCY, HAPPY yelp]
[GRAY, ERZA gasp]
[LUCY, HAPPY, NATSU scream]
[FROSCH, LECTOR whimper]
[GRAY, ERZA gasp]
[SOLDIER 224A]
They launched a flare!
[LAHAR]
What happened?
Such monstrous size.
[DORANBOLT] Sorry about
the delay. How goes it?
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[DORANBOLT]
What is that thing?
I've no idea.
But Fairy Tail and Sabertooth
are fighting it as we speak.
Go to them!
Will do.
Make ready the cannons.
We'll support them from here!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[roars]
[STING]
Erza! Where are the others?
They're trapped
somewhere in the ruins.
That isn't good.
[NATSU grunting]
Well, that hurt.
Is everyone down here?
[NATSU]
Nope, it's just us.
Ngh. Are we trapped?
Please, I don't wanna
die in the dark!
[KEMO-KEMO grunts]
Kemo-Kemo! I'm so
glad you're okay!
[rumbling]
[NATSU, KEMO-KEMO yelp]
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[LECTOR, FROSCH, WENDY whimper]
[HAPPY, LUCY, KEMO-KEMO whimper]
--[LUCY grunts]
--[thumping]
[ALL gasp]
Well that's strange.
What is that I'm hearing?
That sound kind of
reminds me of a heartbeat.
I don't hear anything.
There's something in there.
And I think it's coming.
[ALL yelp]
[roars]
We're gonna have to put
this monster down, soon.
Yeah!
Before our friends inside
there get crushed to bits!
Forget "soon." It's now.
[ERZA yells]
[GRAY]
Ice Cannon!
[MONSTER 224A roars]
You ready?
Let's go! Shadow Dragon...
White Dragon...
[ROGUE, STING]
Roar!
[MONSTER 224A roars]
Sting's as good at
kickin' butts as ever!
Yup, and so is Rogue!
[ALL gasp]
[HAPPY]
This is... amazing!
[NATSU] Looks cool.
Too bad we can't read it.
[LUCY] Actually, these words
are in the same script
as the tablet Jura showed us.
[KEMO-KEMO gasps]
--[thumping]
--[MONSTER 224A roars]
[WENDY sighs]
You okay?
[ERZA gasps]
Actually no. I can't
move. I'm too tired.
I think I know
what you mean now.
[ERZA, GRAY gasp]
[WENDY grunts]
You're injured. What happened?
I've no idea!
They both keeled over
outta nowhere!
It just doesn't make any sense!
[MONSTER 224A roars]
Get them back to
the ships at once!
Right. And after that,
I'll come back for you!
There's no need. Go on.
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[LUCY, NATSU, HAPPY gasp]
This place'll make a puddle
of us before long, so hurry!
I'm going as fast as I can, but
there's so much written here!
--[thumping]
--[gasps]
That sound. Brace yourselves.
Hey. Is it just me, or does
that sound like a heartbeat?
It's not just you.
[thumping]
What if this were
a living island?
[HAPPY]
Uh...
[LUCY, NATSU gasp]
Where the heck did all this
weird smoke come from?
[KEMO-KEMO]
Uhhh... Aaah...
[NATSU] Uh, Kemo-Kemo! You
always were a fast grower, but--
[HAPPY]
This is freaky.
This smoke...
[GRAY grunts]
Stay strong, Gray!
You have to fight!
It's way too hard.
[LECTOR, FROSCH groan]
But why? What's happening to us?
[STING]
No. I don't understand.
[ROGUE]
I-I'm beat, Frosch.
[LECTOR]
I'll take it from here, Rogue.
Just as soon as I can move.
[FROSCH]
Me, too...
[SOLDIERS gasping]
Oh no. What could
be causing this?
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[LAHAR]
Is it poison?
How are things on the island?
When I left, their fight
against the serpent raged on.
[LAHAR]
Did it bite them?
[DORANBOLT] No. I'm told that
they fainted without warning.
Just like your men.
I have a theory, but you
aren't going to like it.
You think that this
is some sort of virus.
Find these two a cabin.
[gasps]
[DORANBOLT]
Lahar! Wake up!
[roars]
[NATSU] Hustle, Lucy!
There's more every time!
Just a sec. it's finally
starting to come together.
The tree. A blessing.
And the sun.
Got anything else?
"Protection." "From disaster."
"Poison death." "Cleansing."
Cleansing? And Poison?
What? No, please! I don't
wanna get cleansed!
[LUCY] Hey, Natsu! Hold a
flame to the ceiling for me.
Whoa. That's it.
Whaddaya mean?
[LUCY]
I've seen this picture before.
It's somewhere in this book.
--[MONSTER 224A roars]
--[GRAY, ERZA yelp]
Lucy's not back yet.
[STING]
Her group might be sick, too.
[ROGUE] If they are,
then we're on our own.
[ERZA]
And in trouble.
[HAPPY, LUCY, NATSU gasp]
Natsu!
Fire Dragon Wing Attack!
[HAPPY]
I gotcha!
--[NATSU] You all right?
--[LUCY panting]
[LUCY]
Yeah. Thanks to you guys. Huh?
What is that thing?
I took a shard of
that broken tablet
from Lamia Scale by accident.
But it might actually be useful.
Okay so...
[LUCY] That hole in the wall!
Recognize the shape?
[NATSU] Yeah! It's
exactly the same shape
as that stone tablet
you were workin' on!
You got it! So here's the plan.
[HAPPY grunting]
[LUCY] I could never figure
out what word this was,
since half of it was missing.
But it's a border piece,
so it should line up somewhere.
Just not there. There either.
[DORANBOLT]
Pull yourself together! Get up!
We must send this island
back where it came from.
Go back to the council.
Tell them to sink it.
What about the wizards on it?
This isn't pleasant,
but it must be done.
We can't let the virus
reach the mainland!
But, I can't--!
Who will be left
to save the kingdom
if you become infected yourself?
[gasps]
I'm sorry. Come back
before it's too late.
[LUCY] Come on.
You've gotta fit somewhere.
Look, I found the spot!
[HAPPY, NATSU]
Ah!
[NATSU]
So, what does it say?
[LUCY]
Lemme check and see!
There it is. This means
"sprouting seed."
Not much to work with.
It's everything we need!
The sun confers its
blessing on the tree.
Photosynthesis!
A poison, which would
cause disaster,
can be cleansed...
...by this one thing.
The sprouting seed!
[KEMO-KEMO]
Aaaah...
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Whoa...
"Protector?"
[KEMO-KEMO]
Ooooh...
Wha...?
Hold on a second! Is this...
...where you come from?
[KEMO-KEMO]
Ah!
[ROGUE]
Lector, Frosch! Say something!
[STING]
This sucks! I can't even stand!
I'd say this was a virus,
but how could it
strike so quickly?
[GRAY] Whatever you're up to,
Natsu, it better be good.
[roars]
[gasps]
[GRAY, ERZA grunt]
[STING grunts]
C'mon Rogue!
[ROGUE]
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[yelps]
[NATSU grunts]
[HAPPY, LUCY, NATSU scream]
[HAPPY]
We're gonna die!
[LUCY whimpers]
[LUCY, NATSU gasp]
[KEMO-KEMO grunts]
--[LUCY, NATSU gasp]
--He's gigantic!
[gasps] The protector. It's you.
[KEMO-KEMO screams]
[KEMO-KEMO] That thing that
I'd forgotten: it came back.
I finally understand
what it is that I am.
And what I was born to do.
Knowing what will happen next.
It doesn't make me
less afraid. Still,
I'll carry out the task
that I was meant for.
I was never once
an "it" to Natsu.
I was family. Now I can
protect him and make him proud.
[roars]
[KEMO-KEMO roars]
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[LUCY, NATSU panting]
[NATSU]
Erza! Gray!
We've fallen ill.
You look awful!
So this smoke really is poison,
I totally called it!
Pull yourselves together,
guys, we gotta move!
[roars]
[KEMO-KEMO roars]
You've got it wrong!
We breathed a ton of
that smoke and we're fine!
Huh?
[LUCY] That smoke comes from
Kemo-Kemo's body, right?
We were underground
with him for hours!
Everyone else got sick.
But the three of us had
a steady supply of antidote.
That smoke you're afraid of!
This island's alive and
it's releasing a virus.
But Kemo-Kemo's breath should
cleanse the whole place!
I think it's working.
[GRAY] That thing over there.
Is that Kemo-Kemo?
[LUCY] I'm beginning to think
that he's not even an animal.
Strange. What happened?
No way. My sickness is gone.
Yes, so is mine.
[LUCY] I think that
he's a Nature Spirit.
And that he'll stop this virus
in its tracks every time
this island rises from the sea.
[roars]
Will ya look at that?
He's was protectin' us when
we didn't even know it.
--[GRAY, ERZA grunt]
--[STING, ROGUE gasp]
[KEMO-KEMO roars]
Don't worry, pal!
You don't hafta fight
that thing alone!
Let's back him up, Happy!
[HAPPY]
Aye!
[roars]
C'mon!
[HAPPY]
Aye, sir!
[NATSU grunts]
All right, Kemo-Kemo!
Let's give this thing
an ultra-warm welcome!
[KEMO-KEMO roars]
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Roar!
[MONSTER 224A roars]
[LUCY]
Something underneath the waves
has caused this island to sink
and surface for millennia.
And Every time it rises up,
it bears a poison from the sea.
Long ago, people built
a civilization here,
unaware of the calamity
awaiting them.
They would've died out quickly,
but Kemo-Kemo saved them!
Crazy. Even after all that time.
When the island rises,
so does he. To cleanse it!
Let's finish him!
[roars]
Flame Lotus:
Exploding Flame Blade!
[MONSTER 224A groans]
[LAHAR, CARLA, WENDY gasp]
Where are Natsu and the others?
Still On the island.
[CARLA, WENDY gasp]
[ALL grunting]
[NATSU]
We kicked its butt!
You just keep gettin'
more awesome!
Hey. Somethin' wrong?
Yo. What's the deal, bud?
Did it hurt'cha?
[rumbling]
It's starting to sink!
[ALL gasp]
[WENDY gasps]
What do we do?
C'mon Natsu, we gotta go!
This island is definitely
sinking fast!
[LECTOR]
Let's get outta here!
[FROSCH] His friend
won't fit on the boat.
Don't do this, Kemo-Kemo!
We're family!
[HAPPY]
Something's changed.
[NATSU] What's wrong?
We can figure it out!
Can you hear me?
[LUCY, GRAY, ERZA gasp]
Uh... That's weird.
[KEMO-KEMO]
Natsu.
[gasps] Wait.
You know how to talk?
[KEMO-KEMO]
I didn't when I first hatched.
It's one of a few things
that I'd forgotten.
Like what I am. My duty.
[HAPPY]
Your duty?
[NATSU] Glad you remembered.
Come on! Let's go home!
[KEMO-KEMO]
I wish I could.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[KEMO-KEMO]
But look at me.
My body's fused into the forest.
When the island sinks,
I'll go down with it.
There's gotta be another way!
I'm going to absorb
the last of the virus.
By the time it's done,
we'll be beneath the sea.
You should go.
No way! Not unless
you're comin' too!
[KEMO-KEMO]
I'm so sorry.
[NATSU]
Why would you be sorry?
[KEMO-KEMO] Because I won't
be able to protect you,
ever again.
You need to escape
while you still can.
This is goodbye, Natsu.
The hell it is, you punk!
I'm not gonna leave you here!
He's gonna stay?
You can still change your mind!
Just come back home, please!
Natsu, I was... in Fairy Tail...
What's that?
I was a member, too, right?
'Course you were! You still are!
Fairy Tail is a family
and you're a part of it.
That isn't gonna change,
not ever!
Thank you. For being my daddy.
Hey. Say somethin'.
Just one more thing! I--
Natsu!
[ERZA]
I couldn't do it. I let him die!
Let's go home.
Try and make me!
[gasps]
A Kemo-Kemo... acorn?
Time to go.
I failed. He was
like family to me.
But I couldn't save him.
Not so. You did right by him.
Think about the people
of that island.
Kemo-Kemo saved them
and yet they're gone today.
That doesn't mean
he failed them.
He gave them time
to love and to grow.
Exactly what you gave him.
She's right.
You helped him find his purpose
and you had fun along the way.
Hope we meet again.
Sometime soon.
[NATSU]
Don't forget to lock the door!
[HAPPY]
Aye, sir!
[HAPPY] Think they'll have
any cool jobs posted today?
[NATSU]
'Course they will!
[HAPPY]
Help me, Natsu!
[NATSU laughs] You don't need
help. You've got a killer afro!
[HAPPY] Yeah, no, it's
goin' haywire 'cause of
all this static electricity.
[NATSU] It really is
a good look, though.
You should keep it.
[HAPPY] Don't be stupid!
Tamp it down for me, will ya?
[NATSU] All right, fine.
Yow! It zapped me!
[HAPPY]
Sheesh, are you okay?
[NATSU] Yeah, sure.
That gave me an idea though.
[HAPPY] My electric hair
must've given you a brain jolt!
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Next Time: "Lightning Man."
[NATSU] So, since the afro's
here to stay and all,
can I call ya 'Froppy?'
[HAPPY] Let's keep my name out
of this discussion, salmon-top.