[tide crashing in]
[ERZA]
I can't believe this.
[NATSU] Three months
training, wasted!
[HAPPY] Just cause we spent one
day in the
Celestial Spirit World.
This sucks.
[GRAY] Could someone send
us back in time for once?
What are we gonna do?
Princess!
I may have the answer!
[VIRGO] More blocks!
Or maybe you should
tighten the ropes?
[LUCY] Just leave.
♪
[NARRATOR]
Welcome to the hall of
the wizard guild, Lamia Scale.
[OHBA]
You kids have no shame!
That's the only explanation.
Why else would you be content
with second place every year?
[NARRATOR]
This woman is Ohba Babasahma.
Lamia Scale's wise,
and loud, master.
[OHBA] We may have
seen it as just fun and
games before, but not
this time, you hear me?
I'm going to whip you
ankle biters into shape!
Shut up, Ohba!
Can't call it a day without
the hag going senile.
[OHBA] Lyon and Jura!
I want you two in
the games this year!
Alright. The hag
says jump, we jump.
Well, the festival
should be a
nice distraction,
if nothing else.
If Lyon and Jura enter,
we're sure to win!
Awesome!
I can already taste victory!
[MALE WIZARD 154C] Look out
Fiore, we're after number one!
[BOB] So, did you hear?
The hag from Lamia
decided to toss the
Wizard Saint Jura into the
Grand Magic Games this year.
[NARRATOR] As you may
recall, this rosy-cheeked
gentleman is Master Bob,
the leader of the
Blue Pegasus guild.
[ICHIYA] Man.
That reeks of a
distressing parfum.
[BOB] It throws
a nasty little wrench
in our plans to win,
that's for sure.
[ICHIYA] Well, then.
How about we unleash our
own little wrench in return?
Tell me you're
not serial, hun.
[ICHIYA] Super-serial.
There's a dangerous
parfum clouding the games.
We should go and sniff it out.
[NARRATOR] At Sabertooth,
The Dragon Slayer duo,
Sting and Rogue,receive
news from their Exceeds.
For real?
Natsu and the others are
entering the Grand Magic Games?
Yep, yep, that's
the rumor that's
been goin' around
Magnolia, anyway.
I heard it with my own ears!
Things just got a
whole lot more interesting!
This'll be awesome!
I couldn't care less.
[NARRATOR] Master Ivan
of Raven Tail has also
heard the rumors, and has
hatched a plan of his own.
[IVAN] For seven long years
you've made me wait, Makarov.
[IVAN] The time of
judgment, our chance
to blacken and crush
the fairies, has come!
I can't wait
'til the games!
I can hardly contain myself.
[HAPPY] For All the Time
We Missed Each Other!
[DROY] We've only got
five days left until the games!
How are we supposed to win?
Well, you aren't gonna
do it by stuffin' your face!
I guess we'll be sittin'
on the side-lines
while everyone else
competes in the games.
How am I supposed
to catch up with
Lily when he has
a three month lead?
I didn't know you
cared about that!
It's not too late! We still
have five days to train!
It'll be Hell-on-Earth,
so prepare yourselves!
You may not survive!
I didn't live this long
just to die from a workout!
Sounds good to me!
Do your worst, Erza!
I'm ready to feel the burn!
Yes, that's
the spirit, Natsu!
We'll start with some running!
A bird?
[GRAY] Check it out, there's
something around its leg.
[NATSU] It's a note.
A love letter maybe?
[JUVIA] You could have just
given it to me directly, Gray!
Yeah, like I wrote it!
[HAPPY] Here we go.
"Hey, Fairy Tail.
You better come to the broken
suspension bridge
on the western hill!"
[NATSU] Dumb note's
not the boss of us!
[GRAY] No kiddin'.
I don't care for their tone.
Not one bit.
[WENDY]
What should we do?
Why ignore it, of course!
I think we should go there.
[LEVY] Ya know, this
sounds like a trap to me.
I'm with Levy.
This has 'trap'
written all over it.
We'll just have to see.
Sweet! I was really
hoping she'd say that.
[ERZA] This must be the
broken suspension bridge.
Cowards must have taken off.
Why are you always
looking for a fight?
Maybe it was just a prank.
Well, now that
that's settled,
let's get back to the beach.
[rumbling]
[JET] What the?
[GRAY] That's a first.
[LEVY ] The bridge.
[JUVIA] It fixed itself!
[GRAY]
Alright, what do we do now?
[ERZA] Obviously we're
supposed to cross it.
[LEVY]
I still say this is a trap.
[WENDY] I wanna go home.
Whoever we're dealing
with is on the other side.
Let's get crossin'!
Is he volunteering?
Sure is. See ya!
[NATSU] Hey!
Don't just shove a
guy when he's not ready!
I could have fallen!
Are you really getting
sick from a freakin' bridge?
[NATSU] Why don't
you come give it a try!
Lousy bridge!
You're not beatin'
me that easily!
[LUCY] Whaddya know?
I thought for sure
it would collapse
the moment someone
stepped on it.
[WENDY] We all thought that.
[NATSU]
You used me as a lab rat?
Now that we know it's
safe to cross,
let's stop wasting time.
Move it people!
[NATSU]
I hope they attack us soon.
[ERZA] Indeed.
A tough opponent will
make for great training.
[GRAY] You know
you're the only ones
obsessed with that, right?
[LUCY] Someone's there!
[JUVIA] Keep your guard up!
Wait.
That smell.
[JELLAL] You came.
[JELLAL] Thank you.
[JELLAL]
It's nice to see you again.
It's really you.
You haven't changed.
Erza.
I take it word of my prison
break reached you some time ago?
Yes.
Please know I never
intended to escape.
Meldy and I didn't
give him much
of a choice in the matter.
That was all you, Ultear!
Don't lump me into
your criminal behavior!
[JUVIA] Meldy.
Long time, no see, Juvia!
[JUVIA] She's grown into a
beautiful and happy young woman.
Jellal broke out of prison?
And with Grimoire
Heart, no less.
[GRAY] Chill out.
They're not our
enemies anymore.
[GRAY] Isn't that right?
Yes.
I committed many sins as a
member of Grimoire Heart.
So many, I doubt I could
ever atone for all of them.
[ULTEAR] So...
I've dedicated myself
to bringing some
measure of peace
to the people I've hurt.
'Til the day I die.
You risked so much
to rescue him from prison.
Because Jellal's one of them.
You don't owe
me anything Ultear.
We were both
possessed by darkness.
It's in the past now.
Jellal. Has your
memory returned?
Every bit of it.
Including my sins.
[JELLAL] Six whole years.
I've been living with the guilt
of all the things I've done.
[JELLAL] Erza.
I'm sorry.
But words can't
erase your pain.
I was the one
controlling Jellal
during the Tower
of Heaven incident.
The blame is mine
so don't punish him.
[ULTEAR] Besides.
I think he's been
through enough as it is.
[JELLAL] I could either spend
the rest of my life in prison.
Or lose my life
and be done with it.
Whatever happened, at least my
penance would have been paid.
But now that you're
free you have a chance
to find a positive
purpose in your life!
[JELLAL] Wendy.
There's no easy way to explain
this, but the Jellal you knew...
He's someone else entirely.
[WENDY] Oh, yeah, don't worry.
We cleared that up a while back.
I found a purpose.
But, I'm not sure that I'd
call it completely positive.
The three of us have
formed a guild of our own.
[ULTEAR] It's an independent
guild, neither officially
recognized nor
aligned with anyone.
[ULTEAR] Its name is Crime
Sorcière, or "witch's crime."
[LEVY] An independent guild?
[HAPPY] What does that mean?
[CARLA] You're not
affiliated with any alliances?
[DROY] Crime Sorcière.
I've heard of you before!
[JET] Yeah, me too.
You guys have taken
down a bunch of
dark guilds over
the past few years.
Unfortunately our
one true goal eludes us.
Zeref.
Dark guilds.
And any evil force
in the world that seeks
to destroy the
lives of innocents.
We'll purge every
one of them so no wizard
will be possessed
by his darkness again.
That's a seriously
righteous cause!
With all the good you've
done, I'm surprised
the Magic Council
won't accept you.
I am a convict.
And Ultear and I used
to be in Grimoire Heart.
[JELLAL] Besides, if we
were to become official,
we wouldn't be able to go
after dark guilds anymore
because of the
Inter-Guild-Conflict Ban Treaty.
[JELLAL] We're far more useful
if we remain as we are now.
[ULTEAR] Anyway,
as much as we'd love to keep
catching up, we brought
you here to ask a favor.
[ULTEAR] Is it true
you'll be entering
the Grand Magic
Games this year?
[NATSU] Yeah.
Why?
[ULTEAR] We can't get near
the coliseum without trouble.
If all of you are willing,
we'd like you to do
something while you're there.
Oh, I get it. You want
someone's autograph.
I'll pretend you
didn't say that.
Every year
we sense unusual
magic power during the games.
We want you to find
out what's behind it.
[NATSU] Are you guys for real?
[LUCY] Guilds from all over
Fiore gather for the games;
the place is full of magic!
[LEVY] Don't you think you
might be a little paranoid?
[JELLAL] We wouldn't
be asking you
if we weren't
absolutely certain.
What's more, the power
we've been sensing
is not only evil but
reminiscent of Zeref.
[ERZA] Zeref? Are you
sure that it's related?
[JELLAL] We believe our
prior involvements with him
have given us the
ability to perceive
any trace of his powers.
I dunno.
Now do you
understand why
ascertaining the
truth is paramount?
If you can track
down the source of
the mysterious energy,
it may help us locate him.
And you'll be compensated,
just like any other job.
[MELDY] Discretion is important.
We don't want the culprit
to know that we're on to them.
So we'll be rooting for you
from behind the scenes.
It sounds like a wild
goose chase, but we'll do it.
[ULTEAR] Thank you.
You sure about this, Erza?
We don't have much choice.
Guilds from all over Fiore will
be gathering around this power.
It could be trouble for us too.
Did we mention we'll
be paying up-front?
[NATSU AND HAPPY]
Food money!
Oh no, nothing
so material.
I've had years to improve
upon my Arc of Time magic,
and can use it to
enhance your abilities.
A "Power Up."
At least, that's
one way to put it.
Though it's not
entirely accurate.
[ULTEAR] Wizards possess
something like an internal
container that determines how
much magic power they can have.
[ULTEAR] Though it's depleted
with every spell you cast,
your body naturally draws in
ether-nano from the surrounding
atmosphere all on
its own and continues
to do so until the
container is full again.
[ULTEAR] But recent research has
revealed that there is a part
of this container, and the magic
it holds, that goes unused.
A "reservoir" of dormant power.
[ULTEAR] They've come
to call these hidden
troves of magic
the "Second Origin."
[NATSU] Seriously?
[ULTEAR] Not only can
my Arc of Time force
your containers to grow,
but I can also grant
you access
your Second Origin.
[ULTEAR] Simply put,
you'll not only be able
to use more powerful magic,
you can keep using it
for longer periods of time.
Whatever you
just said, I liked it!
Be ready.
Unlocking your Second Origin
will involve unimaginable pain.
[LEVY] What's with her eyes?
[NATSU] Dude,
that's totally awesome!
I know we've had
our differences,
but that's water
under the bridge!
By the way,
I'm totally cool with
you pretending to be a chick!
[ULTEAR]
What do you mean pretending?
He still thinks
she's an old man?
[members wildly talking]
[Natsu cries out in pain]
[GRAY] Man I hope
whatever the hell
we just signed up
for is worth it.
[LUCY]
I don't think this is a
very persuasive
advertisement for it.
[ULTEAR] Stay strong.
I know this is tough,
but you still have
a long way to go, Natsu.
[Natsu cries out in pain]
Are you sure he's gonna
get through this thing?
Just what kind
of pain is he feeling?
Wanna Sensory Link
with him and see?
Are you crazy?
[JUVIA THINKS]
I'm so proud of her!
She's even found her own
playful sense of humor!
Do we really have
to go through that, too?
I think I'm gonna cry.
[CARLA] Actually,
you already are.
[DROY] We don't need the extra
strength so we'll be goin'!
[JET] Catch ya later!
[Natsu cries out in pain]
Stay strong.
[CARLA] Do you happen
to know where Erza went?
She and Jellal went somewhere
to be alone for a bit.
[JUVIA THINKS] To be alone?
How about some private
training while they finish?
You're not foolin' me.
[MELDY THINKS]
I was hoping their love
would've blossomed by now.
Erza.
[ERZA] So you remember
everything that happened.
[JELLAL] I do.
[ERZA] Does that include
what happened to Simon?
He died by my hand.
[ERZA] What about
the Nirvana incident?
[JELLAL] Everything.
I remember it as being
trapped in a fog of amnesia.
It's a strange feeling.
Is it accurate
to say I'm speaking
with the Jellal that
I knew as a child?
I'd be happy if
you thought of it that way.
But given my crimes...
I won't blame you if
you keep your distance.
And if you
decide to avenge
Simon, I won't try
to stop you.
My life was
forfeit long ago.
Do you honestly think
Simon would want you to die?
[ERZA] What about
your new guild and
all the good you've
done through it?
Why can't dedicating
your life to fighting
the darkness
be your atonement?
Because I don't think it can.
[ERZA] Why not?
[JELLAL] Don't get me wrong,
when I first created
Crime Sorcière, I hoped
it would bring me peace.
[JELLAL]
But the things I did at the
Tower of Heaven can't
be made right that easily.
[JELLAL] Is there really
a point to what I'm doing?
Will these horrible
thoughts ever go away?
[JELLAL] I feel so lost.
Perhaps it's best if I did die.
[ERZA] You'd be satisfied
with the coward's way out?
[JELLAL] I don't have the
strength to overcome this.
Not like you.
You think you need to
be strong in order to live?
You're wrong!
Life itself is what
gives us strength!
[ERZA] I don't see
the old Jellal before me.
That man was full of life,
he would never
give up without a fight!
[JELLAL] Maybe he's dead then.
[ERZA] Snap out of it!
[JELLAL] It's too late.
[JELLAL] You always
know what to say, don't you?
[ERZA] That's not true at all.
[ERZA] I just stumble through
life one day at a time.
[ERZA] That's all.
[JELLAL] Erza.
[ERZA] I thought I'd
never see you again.
[ERZA] Jellal.
I can't.
I have a fiancée.
[ERZA] Oh no,
I didn't mean to make you
think that I,
or we, should, you know.
Uh.
[JELLAL] No.
I'm the one who should.
Sorry.
A fiancée?
That's a surprise!
Well, congratulations!
That's great!
I'm really happy for you!
[ERZA] Do you love her?
[JELLAL] Yes.
Then live for her sake.
That's your purpose.
[JELLAL] I can do that.
[members groaning in pain]
It seems your magic
has incapacitated the others.
[ULTEAR] How are you
not being affected by it?
I wish we could
help you further,
but we have
to stay on the move.
This is goodbye, for now.
Get a hold of
us by carrier pigeon
if you find anything.
In the meantime, do your
very best at the games!
[ERZA] Yes, we will.
[ULTEAR] Good luck.
And don't forget, we'll be there
in spirit, cheering you on.
[MELDY ] Isn't there some way
we could see it ourselves?
[ULTEAR] We could use disguises.
[JELLAL] Forget it.
Until we meet
again Erza.
Buh-bye!
Give the others our best.
As for Gray.
Look after him for me.
[JELLAL] That power worries me.
If it is related
to Zeref it could
prove deadly to our friends.
Well, having seen what
they can do first hand,
I'm sure they'll find some
way of pulling through.
[MELDY] For real!
So, Jellal.
Where's this
fiancée of yours?
And when do we get to meet her?
[Meldy and Ultear laugh]
[JELLAL] You heard that?
\You know you
could stand to
loosen up a little
every once in a while.
Afraid...?
Or are you
punishing yourself?
Punishment is
what we're all about
or have you
forgotten that fact?
[JELLAL] Together we
decided we cannot fall in
love with those who
walk the path of light.
[JELLAL] As long as
Erza is alive and happy...
That's enough for me.
[MELDY] C'mon, you could've come
up with a better lie than that!
[Ultear laughs]
[ULTEAR] I bet you thought you
sounded so cool, didn't you?
[ERZA] A fiancée.
[ERZA] Always
such a terrible liar.
[ERZA] Guess that means
he's himself again.
[ERZA THINKS] It's for the best.
This is our story.
For now.
[HAPPY] Hey Erza,
look at my drawing!
[Happy cries out]
♪
[NATSU]
We've arrived in Crocus, baby!
[HAPPY] Look at this place!
It's gorgeous!
Just what you'd expect from
the Flower-Blooming Capital!
[NATSU] So this is where the
Grand Magic Games
are bein' held!
Aw man, I can't wait!
[NATSU]
Hold up, who are they?
[HAPPY]
Members of Sabertooth!
They're known as
the Dragon Slayer Duo!
[NATSU] They're Dragon Slayers?
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next time: Crocus,
the Flower-Blooming Capital!
[HAPPY] Y'see those
weird talking cats with 'em?
They keep calling me
names and being big ol' jerks!
Can I please scratch
their eyes out?
[NATSU] Uh, you're a
"weird talking cat" too, bud.