♪
He's from Fairy Tail.
Yeah. But why?
You really don't wanna tangle
with our master, you runt.
That guy's
gonna get murdered.
Yeah, I don't
wanna watch this.
[JIEMMA] Did you truly come here
to challenge me? Very foolish.
I came here to teach you not
to turn your back on people
you're supposed to care for.
So you'd better listen.
[ROGUE] Is he
talking about Yukino?
[STING] Where does he get off?
How our guild operates is
none of his damn business.
[JIEMMA] I don't know
what you're talking about.
But it sounds to me
like you think everyone else
should behave by your
personal moral code.
How the hell do you not
know what I'm talking about?
Hey Doebengal.
Deal with this intruder.
Yes, Sir.
What, are you scared?
I don't feel
like wasting my time
disposing of an insect like you.
I am the master of this guild,
so if you wish to challenge me,
you must prove yourself
to be a worthy adversary.
[HAPPY] Pandemonium!
Don't hide behind
your flunkies; fight me!
[DOBENGAL] I won't
let you near our master!
[DOBENGAL] Although I may
not be participating in
the Grand Magic
Games this year...
[DOBENGAL] I am just as
skilled in battle as those
who represent our guild.
[DOBENGAL] Now you will taste
the true power of Sabertooth!
You're hiding too?
[DOBENGAL] I suggest
you leave at once
or face the consequences! Now!
[NATSU] Outta my way!
[NATSU] I ain't got
business with you, pal!
[SABERTOOTH GUY 166A] Holy crap!
[SABERTOOTH GUY 166B]
He beat Dobengal?
Whoa!
He just took out one
of the toughest guys
in our guild like
he was nothin'!
[JIEMMA growls]
Master. I'll take him.
You'll stay
out of this!
[JIEMMA] No one in my guild
has your kind of spirit, boy.
It's interesting.
But spirit is not enough.
[NATSU yells]
[NATSU] Lightning Flame
Dragon. Firing Hammer!
♪
Minerva!
Milady?
Certainly you'll agree.
This little quarrel of
ours has gone too far.
What?
How dare you get in my way!
This does not concern you.
Please forgive me.
[MINERVA] You could
easily defeat this man,
so I'm not doing this
for your sake, father.
[NATSU] He's your dad?
But we must take into
consideration how this
altercation would appear
to the outside world.
Despite the fact
that you are clearly
the aggressor in this situation,
our master killing
another competitor
would leave Sabertooth
in an awkward position,
to say the very least.
[MINERVA] It would certainly
put a damper on the games.
You know what I think?
You're scared of seeing
this geezer get put down!
[MINERVA] You have enraged
both my father and his men.
And they are not
the types to take
this kind of
provocation lightly.
What do you say?
Will you allow me to resolve
this unpleasantness
in a peaceful manner?
[grunts]
[MINERVA] Be aware. That is
also the only way your kitten
will be returned
to you unharmed.
[wailing]
Happy!
[HAPPY crying] Sorry, Natsu!
Damn it!
[MINERVA] You seem to have
taken out your anger on
quite a few of our members.
But I am willing to overlook
this incident entirely,
if you'll cooperate.
Behave like a grownup
and we can continue
the games like nothing happened.
[growling lowly]
[crying]
Oh, Natsu!
[HAPPY] I'm sorry. They
caught me by surprise!
Aw. Don't worry, little buddy.
I should be apologizing for
leaving you behind like that.
It's okay!
Let's get outta here.
[HAPPY] Aye.
You've got some serious
guts for such a fool.
We can settle this matter once
and for all inside the arena.
Where we'll
show you no mercy.
[NATSU] Fine, but
you'll never beat us.
We're at a whole other level.
'Cause a real guild...
treats its members like family.
[NATSU] That's why
I came here tonight.
[ROGUE] He may be right,
but that's not the way
we treat each other here.
[STING] That was crazy. He's way
stronger than I ever thought.
Hey! I call
first game tomorrow!
And I'm gonna make sure
those Fairy Tail punks
pay for what they did!
Your Black Lightning shall
make their very souls tremble.
Indeed, we shall
respond accordingly
to this act
of disrespect.
[MINERVA] Although I must admit
disturbances such as these
do keep things exciting.
And Since Yukino
is no longer with us...
I shall take it upon
myself to fill her vacancy.
What? You went
and picked a fight
with the master of Sabertooth?
Yeah. But I had to
stop before I really
got a chance to lay into him.
That geezer's lucky that
I'm such a reasonable guy.
No, I'm the
reason he stopped.
It's because I let
those jerks kidnap me.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's far better that
it ended that way.
Seriously. If Natsu
had actually injured
anybody on their team,
our entire guild could've
been kicked out of
the games or worse.
Yeah. As a matter of fact,
the old guy's daughter,
Minerva, was saying something
almost exactly like that.
I can't believe you'd
be that much of an idiot!
Do you even have a
brain in your head?
Obviously not!
Tell him, Gray!
If he doesn't listen,
you can beat it into him!
You need to stop and
think before you ever try
to pull another
crazy stunt like that!
I mean, why do you
get to have all the fun?
I would've loved to beat
the snot outta those guys!
[LUCY] You totally
missed the point!
I know you both
have your reasons
for being angry with them,
but you have to save it for
the competition, you understand?
I wouldn't have
ever hurt anybody.
I just wanted to get
in that pretty boy's face
and let him know I ain't
losing to him again.
Maybe just scare
him a little bit!
Anyway, they are gonna
pay for what they did.
Being in a guild with
somebody means that you never
turn your back on them,
no matter what.
There's a big difference
between strict and cruel.
I would say they crossed
the line with the way
they treated that
poor girl this evening.
Completely uncalled for.
After she was
humiliated like that,
she still came over
here and tried to give me
her Celestial gate keys
as an act of kindness.
I wonder if she even
has anywhere else to go.
I'm worried about her.
Well she can't ever go back
to her guild, that's for sure.
Those bastards. How can they
treat somebody like that?
Screw the games, I'm goin' back!
[GRAY] Alright! Count me in!
Are both of you that stupid?
[WENDY] You need
to do like Erza said
and settle the
score in the games!
And now that this foolishness
has happened tonight,
we can rightfully expect that
every member of Sabertooth
will have a personal
vendetta against our guild!
[ERZA] It's natural
that everyone competing,
regardless of their affiliation,
brings their own motivations
and emotions into the arena.
So ya wanna
play tough, do ya?
You're never
gonna stop us!
Would you guys quit
screwin' around?
Uh!
This is a serious situation--
[ALL] Uh.
The next person
that hits me...
[ERZA] is dead!
[NATSU and GRAY] Sorry, Ma'am!
[MALE CITIZEN 166D]
Did you hear what happened?
[MALE CITIZEN 166E]
You mean last night?
[FEMALE CITIZEN 166A]
What was it?
Some nutjob went
over to the inn where
Sabertooth is staying and just
started tearing up the place.
What kind of idiot
would pick a fight
with those guys?
Must have a death wish.
[BOTH laughing]
[MALE CITIZEN 166D]
I know, right?
[FEMALE CITIZEN 166A] There's
always fights and stuff
outside the tournament.
[MALE CITIZEN 166E] Yeah,
well they need to do it
out on the street and
entertain the rest of us.
[MALE and FEMALE CITIZEN laugh]
[YUKINO] Was it Natsu?
[NATSU] Any guild
that makes a friend cry...
doesn't get to
call itself a guild!
[YUKINO] No way. Wow.
♪
Welcome to day three
of the Grand Magic Games!
That puts us at
the halfway point.
How are we ever going to
top the dramatic fights
and eye candy of
the last two days?
I personally, will be on my best
behavior around today's guest.
From the Magic Council,
it's Marshal Lahar.
It's been quite a while.
Thank you for
having me here.
As Chief Marshal of the
Custody Enforcement Unit,
your job is catching the
bad guys, isn't that right?
Yes. And let me
remind any would be cheaters
that I'm watching you.
[CROWD laughs]
[CHAPATI] That's right, he's got
eyes in the back of his head,
and he never sleeps,
so no funny stuff!
Damn you, Lahar.
Just had to drag me with you.
They want you to be a guest
at the Grand Magic Games?
What'd you tell them?
I told them I'd be happy to.
You should come along
with me. It will be fun.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
The full ranks of
Fairy Tail will be
participating this year.
Wouldn't you like to see
them all alive and well?
[DORANBOLT] Of course I would.
But, they don't want to see me.
[LAHAR] How many times do I have
to tell you, that's in the past?
Besides, you left them
to save your own life.
Everybody is looking
towards the future.
We learn from our
experiences and move ahead.
You should, too.
Oh, no! We're
gonna be so late!
I told you, tomcat,
we didn't have enough time
to stop and buy food!
It just smelled so yummy,
that I couldn't resist it!
[ROMEO] Quit flapping your
gums and move your feet!
[CHAPATI] Let's kick off this
hump day with a game that's
sure to be exciting. One
that we call... Pandemonium!
What the heck's
"pandemonium" mean anyway?
[CARLA] Usually it means chaos
or panic. But sometimes it can
be used to refer to a
den of demons or monsters.
Maybe it'll be set
up like some sort of
haunted house game. The
players walk down a long
dark hallway,
when all of a sudden...
A scary ghost
pops out of nowhere!
Whoa. I might be too
scared to even watch this one.
[MAVIS] A game like that
sounds terrifying to me.
[ROMEO, HAPPY, and CARLA] Huh?
No offense, but aren't
you a ghost yourself?
[CHAPATI] As usual, we will
have just one member from
each team competing.
So please choose wisely.
I got this one. I'm
still pretty fired up from
what went down last night.
You did yesterday's round,
so it's not your turn!
Yeah Natsu, you're not
the only one who would
love to get some sweet payback!
Right. So I'll play then.
I'm certain that you'd only
complicate the matter further
if you were to compete.
Alright! Go and
get us a win, Erza!
Yeah, you've got this!
That is so unfair,
I called this one!
The decision's been made,
so would ya shut up?
I think I should be the
one to go in for our team.
Well I think I should.
I gotta redeem
myself after yesterday.
Why are you
here anyway, Cana?
I thought you were
a reserve member.
Yeah, what happened
to Mystogan?
I know he's shy but no
one's seen him at all today.
The guest announcer is the
same guy who arrested him,
so he decided to
sit this one out today.
Makes sense to me.
Hey, if Erzy's gonna be
going in for her team,
I wanna play against her!
Fine, I'll allow it.
[MILLIANNA] Sorry Erzy,
but I'm gonna beat ya!
That so?
I have never stopped
hating Jellal.
[MILLIANNA]
He used us like tools.
He took Simon away from us.
For all those sins...
he has to pay!
[ERZA] I mustn't lose focus!
[CHAPATI] Putting her paws onto
the field for Mermaid Heel,
it's Millianna!
Hey, I remember her!
So do I.
I guess she was the
one wearin' the hood.
So she finally
joined a guild?
[ALEXEI] The Council is
watching, so be careful
not to draw their
attention, Obra.
I should go. For my fans.
[FEMALE CROWD cheers]
I said that I was gonna
take this one last night.
I'll give them all a
taste of my Black Lightning
they're never gonna forget!
Try not to get
ahead of yourself.
We don't even know
what this game entails.
[RUFUS chuckles]
[STING] It doesn't
matter to me.
If Natsu's not competing, then
I don't really care who goes.
Jura's gonna
play in this round?
It's what the
hag wanted, so yes.
My poor sock.
Just buy a new one, dummy!
[JURA] Victory is mine.
[CHAPATI] All of the
competitors have been chosen!
From Sabertooth, Olga!
From Lamia Scale, Jura!
From Blue Pegasus, Hibiki!
From Raven Tail, Obra!
From Mermaid Heel, Millianna!
From Quatro Puppy, Novali!
From Fairy Tail A, Erza!
From Fairy Tail B, Cana!
Let's all give them a big
round of applause, folks!
[CROWD cheering]
♪
What is this?
I don't know.
[HIBIKI] I'll see what
Archive brings up.
[explosion or rumble]
[MATO] Before you
stands a castle filled with
vicious monsters.
That's Pandemonium!
Holy crap!
I take it we're to do
battle with these monsters?
[MATO]
Yes! You are correct, sir!
[CROWD gasps]
[MATO] One hundred
terrifying beasts are lurking
within the castle walls.
But don't panic,
there's no danger of them
escaping and
attacking the crowd.
They're magical projections we
created solely for this game!
They are classified by
their degree of difficulty.
We have five classes:
D, C, B, A, and S!
The distribution
breakdown is shown here.
To give you an example,
let me show you how strong
a D-Class monster is!
They're the weakest, remember.
[chuckles]
[screaming]
[MATO] The Pandemonium castle
is filled to the brim with
these vile creatures and many
more that are far stronger!
One hundred monsters await you!
I know he said that they
were all magical projections,
but they can probably still
hurt people, can't they?
I just hope Erza and
Cana come out unscathed.
I'm pretty sure they can
take care of themselves,
but it's still scary.
All these games just get
more and more extravagant!
It's a little too much,
if you want my opinion.
[CROWD chatter]
[MATO] Monsters of a higher
class are two times stronger
than the ones beneath them.
So if you think that
D-class guy looked nasty,
you'll lose your mind when the
S-class rears its ugly head.
I'm not even sure that a Wizard
Saint could beat one of those.
Hm.
[MATO] You will all take
turns in choosing the number
of monsters that you
wish to fight in each round.
We call this, the competitor's
"right to challenge."
So we make the choice?
[MATO] That is correct!
So, for instance, if you say you
want to fight three monsters,
then, lo and behold, there will
be three waiting inside for you.
You will go in alone, of course.
If you successfully vanquish
those three creatures,
you will then be
awarded three points!
The next competitor in the
rotation will choose a number
out of the ninety-seven that
still remain to challenge.
And then the process repeats!
The game will end when
either all the monsters
[MATO] have been cleared,
or at the point that everyone
runs out of magic power;
whichever comes first.
So there's some
math involved, huh?
[MATO] Yes, to a degree.
After the first round,
choosing your numbers wisely
will become a
bit more important.
But you'd do
well to remember that
not all of these monsters
are created equal.
[MATO] Whether you
choose to test your skills
against five monsters,
or only one,
they will be chosen
completely at random.
So that means we'll
have to strategize
and use our heads to
try to avoid going against
the S-class guys in there.
He just told us that they're
gonna be chosen at random,
so how the hell can you
use any kind of strategy?
You can't. But I sure can.
I know all about probability.
And my Archive magic
will come in handy.
[MATO] Although the
higher-ranked creatures
are more difficult, points
are determined solely by
the number of monsters
you can defeat.
[MATO] Once you enter
the castle, you will not
be allowed to leave
until you've successfully
completed your challenge.
[CANA] So what happens if
you don't beat all of them
and get knocked out inside?
[MATO] You'll keep all
the points you accumulated
in the previous rounds.
But you'll also
be out of the game.
No points will be awarded
if you beat less than
the number you
challenged that round.
It would seem that
not getting overzealous
with your challenges is key.
But if you only fight
one monster in every round
there's no way that
you can get ahead.
And they also need to
factor in how much magic power
they'll be able to
recover between each round.
This game is way more
complicated than it seems.
I'm curious to see how many
our members will choose.
I think they'll both
do a really good job.
[MATO] Now, to decide
the order you'll go in,
I'd like everyone
to please draw a straw!
[beep]
I'm going first!
Man you're lucky.
And I'd be willing to bet
that means you'll also get
the most amount of turns.
Meanwhile, I'll be
stuck back at number eight.
[ERZA] Interesting. I had
assumed victory in this event
relied entirely on
the luck of the draw.
[MATO] It's far more than that.
You have to consider pacing,
your opponents' strength,
the likelihood of getting
a really nasty monster.
The list goes on and on.
It is quite a complex
game if you think about it.
No. In fact, this is
no longer even a game.
[MATO] Huh?
Inside this castle...
wait one hundred monsters.
I choose to challenge...
all of them!
[MILLIANA gasps]
[CANA, HIBIKI, and NOVALI] Huh?
[MATO] Say what?
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH laughing]
[NATSU] Erza is one scary chick!
One hundred monsters on her own?
[HAPPY] Well, she's kind of
a monster herself, isn't she?
[NATSU]
Whoa, she's got tons of armor!
[HAPPY] Heaven's Wheel,
Black Wing, Flame Empress,
Sea Empress, Flight,
Adamantine, Giant, Morning Star.
[NATSU] Ya think
she's got Troll Armor
and Wicked Witch Armor, too?
[HAPPY] That kinda sounds
like you're makin' fun of her.
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
"One Hundred Against One!"
[HAPPY] I wonder if
the other guys are sad
that they don't get
to fight any monsters.
[NATSU] I dunno.
They'll probably get over it
pretty quickly.