- HEY GUYS! READY FOR
SOME MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT WHEN
YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS
ON IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO
CLOSE TO THE TV!
- Gray: PREVIOUSLY
ON FAIRY TAIL!
- Happy: WE'RE IN BIG TROUBLE
WITH THE MAGIC COUNCIL!
- YEAH, IT'S NOT SURPRISING
AFTER ALL THAT CRAZY DAMAGE
WE'VE CAUSED.
- Lavian: THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
- Happy: THE WORST PART
IS MASTER MAKAROV
IS GONNA BE PUT ON TRIAL!
- Lavian: THANK YOU
SO VERY MUCH!
- Gray: HOLD ON.
WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( snoring )
- UH, MISTER MAKAROV, HELLO?
- HERE!
- COURT IS IN SESSION, SIR!
AND WE HAVE A VERY STRICT POLICY
OF "NO SLEEPING"
WHILE ON THE STAND!
- SORRY ABOUT THAT!
- Makarov: PHANTOM LORD'S
TO BE DISBANDED,
AND JOSE STRIPPED OF HIS TITLE
AS ONE OF THE WIZARD SAINTS.
PRETTY MUCH WHAT I EXPECTED.
BUT THEN, FAIRY TAIL
WAS FOUND INNOCENT,
WHICH CAME AS A BIT OF
A SURPRISE TO ME.
- I SPOKE IN DEFENSE OF
YOUR CHARACTER, MOCKY.
I HOPE YA APPRECIATE THAT.
- YA KNOW I'M GLAD
FOR THE SUPPORT, YAJ.
I'D LIKE IT IF YA COULD
DROP BY THE GUILD
ONCE IT'S BEEN REPAIRED,
AND I'LL TREAT YA TO SOME RAMEN.
I COULD GO FOR A FAIRY RAMEN
WITH TWELVE SLICES
OF ROASTED PORK.
THAT'S KINDA PUSHING IT,
DON'T YA THINK?
- DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THE PENALTY IS
FOR VIOLATING THE FOURTH CLAUSE
OF YOUR GUILD CHARTER?
- ALL RIGHT, I GET THE POINT!
YOU CAN HAVE TWENTY SLICES!
BETTER YET, MAKE IT THIRTY!
TWELVE PORK SLICES WILL BE FINE.
- Shitou: LISTEN, I THINK
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO REIN IT IN.
WE'RE JUST NOT AS YOUNG AS
WE USED TO BE, YOU KNOW.
DON'T TELL ME THAT
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN?
- ABOUT WHAT?
- WHAT HAPPENED TO OUR OLD PAL.
- WHO? ROB? 'COURSE NOT.
- THOSE WERE THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
THE TEAM OF YOU, ME, ROB,
AND PORLYUSICA.
WE WERE ALL SO YOUNG BACK THEN.
JUST A BUNCH OF RECKLESS FOOLS.
BUT WE LIVED EVERY DAY
TO THE FULLEST.
- WE SURE DID.
FAIRY TAIL WAS A GREAT PLACE
TO BE UNTIL ROB LEFT US.
ERZA SOMETIMES
SHARES HER STORIES
OF WHAT HE WAS LIKE IN
HIS LATER YEARS.
- I BROUGHT THIS UP 'CAUSE
THERE'S BEEN INCREASING TALK
THAT FAIRY TAIL'S ANTICS HAVE
BEEN GETTING OUT OF HAND LATELY.
MICHELLO AND ORG HAVE BEEN
MAKING NOISE IN THE COUNCIL,
ABOUT WANTING TO
DISBAND THE GUILD.
A MAN YOUR AGE SHOULDN'T BE
DEALING WITH ALL THESE PROBLEMS.
IT'S TOO MUCH STRESS.
YOU WON'T DO ANYONE ANY
GOOD IF YOU'RE DEAD.
DON'T GO LIKE ROB.
SERIOUSLY, YOU'VE GOTTA
STEP DOWN SOON.
YOU'RE NOT A KID ANYMORE.
- Happy: NEXT GENERATION!
- LISTEN UP, EVERYONE!
WE'RE TAKING ON JOB REQUESTS
AGAIN, STARTING TODAY!
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE THE MESS
WHILE WE'RE UNDER CONSTRUCTION,
BUT AT LEAST YOU CAN
GET BACK TO WORK!
- ( everybody cheering )
- Lucy: WHAT'S UP WITH THEM?
MOST OF THE TIME THESE GUYS
WOULD JUST BE LOAFING AROUND
THE GUILD HALL ALL DAY.
- ( laughs )
- I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU'VE
SEEN LOKE, HAVE YOU?
- OH, DON'T TELL ME
YOU'VE FALLEN HEAD OVER HEELS
FOR FAIRY TAIL'S
RESIDENT PLAYBOY!
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
IT'S JUST THAT APPARENTLY HE
WAS THE ONE WHO FOUND MY KEYS.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL HIM THANKS
FOR HIS HELP.
- SURE, I'LL LET HIM KNOW
IF I SEE HIM.
SO WERE YOUR CELESTIAL SPIRITS
MAD AT YOU?
YOU KNOW,
FOR DROPPING YOUR KEYS?
- UH, YEAH. YOU COULD SAY THAT.
AND THERE'S ONE
SPIRIT IN PARTICULAR
WHO WAS REALLY PO'ED WITH ME.
- WHAT DID I SAY ABOUT
DROPPING MY KEY, HUH?
- ( Lucy screams )
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT
MAKES MY BUTT STING!
- GOODNESS, ME!
- I COULD COOL IT FOR YA.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE
SEXUAL HARASSMENT TO ME.
- LUCY, CAN YOU SHOW ME
HOW RED YOUR BUTT IS?
- AND WITH THAT COMMENT
YOU'VE CROSSED THE LINE!
- HOW DO YA THINK SHE'LL REACT
IF I MAKE HER BUTT
STING EVEN MORE?
- WHO ARE YOU? THE DEVIL?
- Erza: WHY DON'T YOU
TELL THE OTHERS HOW YOU FEEL?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I HAVE NO PROBLEM TELLING 'EM
WHAT I THINK OF 'EM.
THIS GUILD'S FULL OF NOTHING
BUT LOSERS AND WEAKLINGS!
ESPECIALLY THE TWO
OF YOU MORONS.
YOU WERE PHANTOM'S
PERSONAL PUNCHING BAGS.
YOU KNOW I'M GLAD I NEVER
BOTHERED TO LEARN YOUR NAMES.
WHICH BRINGS ME
TO THE WORST OF THEM ALL,
THE RICH LITTLE PRINCESS WANNABE
WIZARD. THIS WAS YOUR FAULT.
- LAXUS! WOULD YOU SHUT UP?
THE MASTER SAID NO ONE IN THE
GUILD WAS TO BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED, NOT EVEN YOU,
DESPITE THE FACT THAT I
BEGGED YOU TO COME HELP
AND YOU TURNED YOUR BACK ON US!
- STOP YOUR WHINING! THAT FIGHT
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
BUT IF I HAD BEEN THERE,
YOU WOULDN'T BE
DROWNING YOUR SORROWS
IN THIS PILE OF
RUBBLE RIGHT NOW.
- WHY, YOU! NATSU!
- I'VE HEARD ENOUGH OUTTA YOU!
C'MON LAXUS! FIGHT ME
LIKE A MAN! YA GUTLESS COWARD!
- HOW D'YA EXPECT TO FIGHT ME
WHEN YA CAN'T EVEN
TOUCH ME, YA DIMWIT?
I CAN'T WAIT TO INHERIT
THIS PLACE
AND KICK ALL YOU
WEAKLINGS TO THE CURB!
YOUR DAYS IN FAIRY TAIL
ARE NUMBERED, KIDS!
THINGS ARE GONNA BE A WHOLE LOT
DIFFERENT AROUND HERE,
SO I GUESS YOU LOSERS WILL HAVE
TO FIND A NEW PLACE TO HANG OUT.
- WHAT A JERK! WHY WOULD ANYONE
EVER LET HIM TAKE OVER?
- WE MAY NOT HAVE A CHOICE.
LAXUS COULD INHERIT THE GUILD
BECAUSE HE'S THE
MASTER'S GRANDSON.
WHETHER WE LIKE IT OR NOT,
HE'S AT THE TOP OF A SHORT LIST
OF PEOPLE WHO COULD
ASSUME COMMAND,
IF THE MASTER WERE TO RETIRE.
- NO. REALLY?
THAT SUCKS.
IT DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT.
SOMEONE WHO TALKS LIKE THAT
ABOUT HIS FELLOW MEMBERS,
ISN'T WORTHY OF BEING
FAIRY TAIL'S LEADER.
- IT'S BEEN RUMORED MASTER
MAKAROV REFUSES TO RETIRE
FOR THAT VERY REASON.
- WOW. SERIOUSLY?
- MAN, I HATE HIM!
- CALM DOWN. IT'S JUST
A NEEDLESS WASTE OF ENERGY.
LET'S TRY TO GET
YOUR MIND OFF HIM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT TAKING A JOB?
AND WE CAN GET GRAY AND LUCY
TO COME ALONG WITH US!
- DO WHAT?
- HEY, GRAY. YOUR CLOTHES.
- WE'VE ALL BEEN WORKING
TOGETHER
SINCE THE EISENWALD INCIDENT,
SO I GUESS WE'RE A TEAM
OF SORTS NOW.
- IT TOOK HER THIS LONG TO
FIGURE THAT OUT? WE ALL KNEW.
- YEAH, THOSE GUYS HAVE
BEEN JOINED AT THE HIP
FOR A WHILE NOW.
AND THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
SHE CALLED THEM HER TEAM?
- THAT'S ERZA FOR YA!
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
MAKING IT OFFICIAL?
THE FOUR OF US
WORKING AS A TEAM.
WELL, ACTUALLY FIVE
IF WE INCLUDE HAPPY.
- BUT YOU'RE SURE YOU WANT
SOMEONE LIKE ME ON YOUR TEAM?
- NOT SOMEONE LIKE YOU! LUCY,
IT'S GOTTA BE EXACTLY YOU!
- AYE!
- IT JUST WOULDN'T FEEL RIGHT
IF WE DIDN'T HAVE YOU OUT
THERE WITH US, YA KNOW?
- NOW THAT THEY
FINALLY REALIZE IT,
I GUESS THEY'RE OFFICIALLY
OUR STRONGEST TEAM.
- YEAH, IT'S ABOUT TIME!
- IS LUCY REALLY ONE OF
OUR STRONGEST?
- I KNOW I'D BE DONE FOR
IF SHE SICCED THAT
PSYCHO AQUARIUS ON ME!
- SHE'S GOT A REAL SHARP
TONGUE, TOO!
- YEAH, SHE'S ONE OF THE BEST
IN THE GUILD.
- I GOTTA TEAM UP WITH HIM?
- PROBLEM, BOYS?
- NO! WE'RE ABSOLUTELY THRILLED!
- I'VE ALREADY GOT A JOB
LINED UP FOR US.
TAKING DOWN AN ARCANE CULT IN
THE CASTLE TOWN OF LUPINAS.
WITH ME?
- All: YEAH!
- RETIRE, HUH?
WITH THE NEW HALL,
PERHAPS THE GUILD NEEDS A NEW
MASTER AS WELL. BUT WHO?
LAXUS? HE'S GOT SOME PERSONAL
ISSUES HE NEEDS TO SORT OUT.
MYSTOGAN. A SILENT RECLUSE
IS HARDLY LEADER MATERIAL.
OF COURSE THERE'S ERZA,
BUT SHE'S STILL RATHER YOUNG.
- OH! THERE YOU ARE, MASTER!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER
FOR YOU!
IT SEEMS THEY'VE DONE IT
AGAIN, SIR!
- DONE WHAT?
- ERZA AND HER TEAM
COMPLETED THE LUPINAS JOB
BUT THEY DESTROYED
HALF THE TOWN!
THE MAGIC COUNCIL IS
DEMANDING THAT YOU SUBMIT
A WRITTEN APOLOGY IMMEDIATELY!
MASTER? IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG?
- I'M NEVER GONNA BE ABLE TO
RETIRE AT THIS RATE!
- YOU'RE LOOKIN' A BIT DOWN
IN THE DUMPS THERE, LUCY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S THAT JOB WE DID
IN LUPINAS.
IT WAS NUTS.
NATSU KEPT SPITTING
FIRE EVERYWHERE,
AND GRAY FROZE THE STUFF
HE MISSED.
THEN ERZA... DON'T GET
ME STARTED ON HER!
- I COULD'VE WARNED YOU
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
- WE WERE A BIGGER MENACE TO THE
TOWN THAN THAT CULT EVER WAS,
AND WE'RE PAYING FOR IT
OUT OF OUR REWARD.
IF THIS KEEPS UP I'M NOT EVEN
GONNA BE ABLE TO COVER MY RENT!
- WELL, I JUST HAPPEN
TO HAVE A SPECIAL JOB
I COULD THROW YOUR WAY.
THIS ONE'S RIGHT UP YOUR ALLEY
AND THE BEST PART IS,
YOUR TEAM WON'T BE ABLE
TO DESTROY ANYTHING!
- YEAH?
- AND SO WE MOVE ON!
- Lucy: WOW, ONIBAS!
WE HAVEN'T BEEN HERE
SINCE THAT WHOLE LULLABY THING!
- Happy: HEY, NATSU, WE'RE HERE!
- Natsu: DON'T MAKE ME MOVE.
- Gray: SO, LEMME MAKE SURE
I GOT THIS RIGHT.
OUR JOB IS SIMPLY USING
OUR MAGIC TO DRAW A CROWD
TO SOME RUNDOWN THEATER?
- Lucy: YEP, NATSU'LL
IMPRESS THE CROWD
WITH HIS FIRE BREATHING,
YOU'LL MAKE
AMAZING ICE SCULPTURES,
AND ERZA'LL RE-EQUIP
INTO DIFFERENT ARMOR!
THEN I'LL HAVE LYRA SING A SONG
THAT'LL MELT THEIR HEARTS.
PEOPLE ARE GONNA COME
FROM MILES AROUND!
IF I EVER FINISH MY NOVEL, I'M
SURE IT WOULD MAKE A GREAT PLAY.
YES! THIS IS GONNA
BE MY BIG CHANCE
TO LEARN ALL I CAN
ABOUT THE STAGE!
- WHOA!
- PRETTY CLASSY, HUH? LET'S GO!
- EXCUSE ME.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'RE THE WIZARDS
FROM FAIRY TAIL, ARE YOU?
- YEP!
- THANK YOU FOR
ACCEPTING THE JOB!
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW
GRATEFUL I AM!
- WELL, WE'LL MAKE SURE
YOU HAVE A PACKED HOUSE!
- ACTUALLY, ABOUT THAT.
UNFORTUNATELY, I'M IN A BIT OF
A PICKLE RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT? ALL OF YOUR ACTORS
JUST WALKED OUT ON YOU?
- YES. THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH!
-THANKS FOR WHAT?
- MY LAST FEW SHOWS HAVE BEEN
COMPLETE AND UTTER FAILURES.
THE REVIEWS HAVE GOTTEN SO BAD,
THE ACTORS ARE
EMBARRASSED TO PERFORM
IN ANOTHER ONE OF
MY PRODUCTIONS.
SO THEY LEFT,
JUST LIKE MY WIFE.
BUT I WON'T GIVE UP
ON MY DREAMS!
THE THEATER IS IN MY BLOOD,
BUT THIS WAS MY
LAST CHANCE TO SHINE!
NOW I CAN NEVER REDEEM MYSELF!
- MAN, I THOUGHT ACTORS WERE
THE DRAMATIC ONES.
- I HAD NO CHOICE. THE
PERFORMANCE HAS BEEN CANCELED.
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH!
- Erza: YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
"THE SHOW MUST GO ON"!
HAVE NO FEAR! WE SHALL PERFORM
IN YOUR PLAY!
- HEY, IS SHE GLOWING?
- AH-- A-- EE-- EWE-- A-- OOH--
AH-- OOH--KAH-- KAY-- KEE-- KU--
- THAT'S SOME WARM UP
YA GOT THERE.
- NOW THAT I
THINK ABOUT IT,
THIS SOUNDS LIKE IT
COULD BE A LOT OF FUN!
- YA WANNA DO IT?
- WELL, THAT SETTLES IT THEN,
WE'RE NOT GONNA LET
YOUR DREAM DIE, SIR!
- REALLY?
WELL, I GUESS I'VE GOT NOTHING
TO LOSE. UGH. WHAT AMATEURS.
- SO, THIS IS WHEN YOU SHOULD BE
THANKING US.
- Lucy: WE'VE ONLY GOT ONE WEEK
UNTIL SHOW TIME!
- I AM PRINCE FREDERICK!
AND I HAVE COME TO
RESCUE THE PRINCESS!
- WHOA, I HAD NO IDEA
ERZA WAS SUCH A GOOD ACTRESS!
IT'S LIKE SHE WAS MADE FOR
THIS PART!
- MAN, WE CAN'T LET HER
STEAL THE SHOW!
- Gray: NO WAY!
- Happy: AYE, SIR!
- Lucy: FROM THAT POINT ON,
WHENEVER WE WEREN'T REHEARSING,
WE WERE HANDING OUT FLIERS
TO ANYBODY WHO'D TAKE ONE,
AND WORKING TIRELESSLY
TO FINISH THE SET.
I GOTTA SAY, IT WAS REALLY HARD
MEMORIZING ALL THOSE LINES.
BUT WE WERE SO EXCITED ABOUT
OUR UPCOMING PERFORMANCE,
THAT WE ENJOYED OURSELVES
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY!
- I HATE TO INTERRUPT,
BUT YOU'VE GOT SOME FANS
THAT ARE HERE TO SEE YOU.
- Everybody: WE HAVE FANS?
- YO!
- WHOA, WHAT'RE ALL OF
YOU DOING HERE?
- WE WOULDN'T MISS YOUR
DEBUT! NOW BREAK A LEG!
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE SEEN A PLAY.
- I REALLY APPRECIATE
THE INVITE, MOCKY.
- LONG TIME NO SEE,
HOW YA DOING, SWEETIE?
- I TAGGED ALONG TO
HECKLE YOU GUYS.
- MEAT, MEAT!
- THE FAKE SALAMANDER?
DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- SO WHATCHA BEEN UP TO, OKRA?
- THAT WOULD BE BORA.
AFTER GETTING A HARSH LESSON
FROM YOUR BLAZING FISTS,
I DECIDED TO CHANGE MY WAYS
AND GIVE UP THE LIFE
OF A MODEL SCOUT.
- YOU DON'T SERIOUSLY THINK
ANYONE'S BUYING THAT, DO YOU?
- WHY ELSE WOULD I RECRUIT
YOUNG LADIES?
- WELL, BECAUSE YOU...
- SHE THOUGHT YOU WERE DOING
DIRTY THINGS WITH 'EM!
- I'LL BE OUT THERE
A-ROOTIN' FOR YA, ME BEAUTY!
- THANK YOU FOR COMING
ALL THIS WAY.
- AR, THAT HURT!
- HOW'S GALUNA TREATING YA?
- IT'S GREAT!
I CAME TO SAY THANKS AGAIN
FOR SAVING OUR VILLAGE.
- ME, TOO!
- EXCUSE ME, YOU'RE FROM
PHANTOM LORD, RIGHT?
- YEAH BUT NATSU
REALLY IMPRESSED US
WHEN HE BEAT UP GAJEEL.
- SO WE CAME TO SEE THE SHOW
AND GIVE YOU THIS.
- IT'S MEAT!
- YOU DO REALIZE IT'S STILL RAW.
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE I COOKED
IT FOR YOU, GIRLY!
- YOU DIDN'T COOK.
- IT LOOKS GREAT!
- NOT YOU EITHER!
I MADE IT FOR THE
LITTLE RED DOGGIE.
- UPPA!
- BUT HE'S A BLUE CAT.
- SO WHEN ARE YOU AND YOUR
FRIENDS GONNA DESTROY THE MOON
FOR US LIKE YA PROMISED?
- HAVEN'T WE BEEN OVER THIS LIKE
A MILLION TIMES, CHIEF?
- BREAK A LEG!
- THANKS, WE WILL!
- I'M BEAT AND THE CURTAIN
HASN'T EVEN GONE UP YET.
- AND THEN.
- Lucy: IT'S TIME FOR
OUR DEBUT PERFORMANCE!
- Announcer: MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION?
- I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER THE LAST
TIME WE HAD A SOLD OUT HOUSE!
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH!
- OHH. I'VE NEVER SUNG IN FRONT
OF AN AUDIENCE THIS BIG BEFORE!
- DON'T BE NERVOUS,
YOU'LL BLOW THEM AWAY!
- ( buzzer buzzes )
- ( singing ) ♪ AGES AGO ♪
♪ THERE LIVED A PRINCE ALONE ♪
♪ HIS HEART CRIED OUT ♪
♪ ITS ECHO RETURNED... ♪
- Shitou: THAT GIRL HAS
SUCH A LOVELY VOICE!
- SIMPLY MARVELOUS!
- ♪ IN A DISTANT LAND ♪
♪ SO FAR AWAY ♪
- YOU'RE A VISION, ME BEAUTY!
- OH, WOW. THAT PRINCE
IS SO DREAMY!
- ♪ SHE NEEDED HIM
TO RESCUE HER ♪
- THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
- SHE'S TOTALLY FREEZING UP!
- SHE'S GOT A MEAN CASE OF
STAGE FRIGHT!
- UH-OH.
- ♪ TO FIND LOVE ♪
- HEAR YE! HEAR, OH-- MY NAME.
I'M A PRINCE. I CAME
TO SAVE THE PRINCESS!
- MEAT GONE BAD!
- WHAT A STIFF PERFORMANCE.
- NAH, MAN, I BETCHA SHE'S JUST
ACTING LIKE SHE'S NERVOUS.
- SHE MUST DO THAT
'LAMAZE METHOD' ACTING.
- YOU'RE NOT BRIGHT, HUH?
- AND I WIELD
THE POWER OF...
- OH NO, SHE SKIPPED WAY AHEAD!
THAT LINE'S FROM A
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT SCENE!
- ERZA'S SO NERVOUS I'M NOT
EVEN SURE IF SHE'S BREATHING!
- I WIELD THE POWER
'CAUSE I HAVE TEN SWORDS!
- BRAVISSIMO, ME BEAUTY!
- THAT'S DIFFERENT.
- WHO KNEW THE THEATER WAS
SUCH A DANGEROUS PLACE?
- ISN'T IT EXCITING?
- SHE'S FALLING APART
OUT THERE, GUYS!
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- WELL, WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE
TO IMPROVISE AROUND HER
AND DO OUR BEST TO
SAVE THE SHOW!
- WHEN DO I GET TO GO ON STAGE?
- SHUT YOUR TRAP!
OH, MY BELOVED PRINCE FREDERICK,
PLEASE SAVE ME!
I'M HELD IN THE
TERRIBLE CLUTCHES
OF THAT FIENDISH BRUTE SEINHART!
- SO WHO'S THIS SEINHART GUY?
- BEATS ME.
- I AM THE GREAT JULIUS!
IF YOU WANT TO SAVE THE PRINCESS
THEN YOU WILL HAVE TO
CROSS BLADES WITH ME!
- Man 1: WHO THE
HECK'S THIS GUY?
- Girl 1: YEAH, WHAT
HAPPENED TO SEINHART?
- THIS PLAY MAKES NO SENSE!
- BUT THEY'RE SUCH
GIFTED ACTORS!
- I CHALLENGE YOU... TO A DUEL.
- WHOA, SHE'S
COMPLETELY LOST IT!
- WAIT, I'VE GOT AN IDEA! OPEN
GATE OF THE CLOCK CONSTELLATION!
HOROLOGIUM!
- ( audience exclaiming )
- WE WILL FIGHT, DUEL!
THE PRINCE SAYS TIMIDLY.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- THE SHOW'S DEAD IN THE WATER
IF BRAVE PRINCE
FREDERICK PASSES OUT
BEFORE HE DUELS
AGAINST THE VILLAIN!
HOW GOOD OF YOU TO COME,
GREAT CLOCK!
THE BRAVE PRINCE IS IN URGENT
NEED OF A MOMENT'S REST.
- FINALLY CAUGHT MY
BREATH. I'M BACK!
- MEET YOUR DOOM!
MY SWORD OF ICE!
- UH, VERY WELL. I WILL ATTACK
YOU WITH... WITH MY TEN SWORDS!
- Gray: I'M OUTTA HERE!
- Girl 2: THAT IS SO WEAK!
- Man 2: DON'T JUST RUN OFF!
- HIS FEAR WAS SO REAL!
- IT LOOKS LIKE JULIUS
GOT COLD FEET!
- I WONDER WHEN
NATSU'S GONNA SHOW.
- PRINCE FREDRICK, THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME!
- PLEASE, LADY YANDERICA,
LETS GET MARRIED
AND HAVE MANY CHILDREN!
LIKE THIRTY-THREE!
- Guy 3: YOU'RE JUMPING THE GUN,
DON'T YA THINK?
- Man 4: WELL, I'M LOST!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Makarov: THESE MODERN PLAYS
ARE PRETTY SURREAL?
- Shitou: I'M REALLY
ENJOYING IT!
- Mirajane: ME, TOO!
THEY'RE BRILLIANT ACTORS!
- THE CALM BEFORE THE STORM
SHALL ENDETH NOWETH!
- Girl 3: HEY, LOOK,
JULIUS IS BACK!
- Man 5: IS "NOWETH"
EVEN A WORD?
- DEATH AWAITS THOU! NOW COME
FORTH AND CHAR HIM, MY DRAGON!
- WELL, THAT'S MY CUE!
I'M A POWERFUL DRAGON!
I WILL DESTROY YOU ALL!
- THERE HE IS!
- RED DOGGIE!
- LET'S VANQUISH THIS BEAST!
- YES! WE SHALL SLAY IT!
- Man 6: YOU SUMMONED
IT, GENIUS!
- Man 7: I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
- I CAN TAKE CARE OF THE DRAGON!
YOU TWO GET TO SAFETY!
- Man 8: THE PRINCESS
IS GONNA SLAY IT?
- THANKS. WE OWE YOU ONE!
- Gray: LATER!
- Man 9: THEY'RE LEAVING
HER BEHIND?
- OH! THEY'RE ELOPING!
- I NEVER KNEW THAT
GRAY WAS SUCH A PLAYER!
- I NEVER KNEW HE LIKED BOYS.
- SO HEAVY.
- ( coughing )
- OH NO, I'M ON FIRE!
HELP ME, GRAY! I NEED ICE!
- I'LL SAVE YA! HERE GOES!
ICE MAKE...
- SHE CUT OFF MY DRESS!
- OH, MY GOODNESS!
- THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH!
- PRINCESS, DO YOU NOW
FEEL ALRIGHT?
- HOW'D YOU END UP GETTING
THE LEAD IN THIS PLAY?
- THAT HURT!
- ( bell ringing )
- GEEZ, WOULD YA CUT IT
OUT, NATSU?
- THE PRINCESS' HOT BODY
TOTALLY MOVES ME!
- AW, YEAH!
- NOW, NOW BOYS!
WHO SAID YOU COULD JUST SHOW UP
AND EMBARRASS ME?
- SORRY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE IN DANGER.
I PROMISED I'D ALWAYS
PROTECT YOU, MISS LUCY,
BUT I'LL VAMOOSE.
- MY SPIRITS ARE CRAZY.
- I HAVE NO CHOICE. PUNISHMENT
AWAITS ALL OF YOU SCOUNDRELS!
- THIS IS WAY OUTTA HAND!
- YES! YES!
- OH, MAN, THIS IS NOT
GONNA BE GOOD.
I KNEW IT!
- OH, MY STARS!
- WHY DOES THIS KEEP HAPPENING?
- MOCKY, TAKE MY ADVICE
AND RETIRE SOON!
- OH, DEAR ME!
- THE CURSE OF THE MOON
IS TO BLAME!
- ( audience cheering )
- THEY LOVED US! YES!
- Lucy: AND SO, ONE WEEK LATER.
- I TRULY CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT A TREMENDOUS HIT
THE SHOW'S BECOME!
ESPECIALLY WITH THESE
LOUSY ACTORS I'VE GOT.
- C'MON MAN, WOULD YOU JUST
GIVE US OUR MONEY ALREADY?
- I CAN'T KEEP DOING THREE
PERFORMANCES A DAY!
- PERK UP! THE SHOW MUST GO ON,
YA LAZY BUMS!
- WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH THIS GUY?
- I'M DONE. I WANNA GO HOME NOW!
- ( closing theme song playing )
- OH, GUESS WHAT?
I'VE BEEN WATCHING
LUCY AND LOKE,
AND I'M PRETTY SURE THEY'RE
FALLIN' IN LOVE!
- ARE YA SURE ABOUT THAT?
'CAUSE HE ALWAYS SEEMS
TO BE GOING OUT OF HIS WAY
TO AVOID HER AS FAR
AS I CAN TELL.
- I DUNNO, HE MAY BE
ONE OF THOSE GUYS
THAT LIKES PLAYIN'
"HARD TO KNIT."
- "HARD TO KNIT"?
YOU SURE YA GOT THAT RIGHT?
IT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE SENSE.
- Natsu and Happy: NEXT TIME:
A STAR REMOVED FROM THE SKY!
- Happy: LUCY AND LOKE SITTING
IN A TREE K--I--S--S--I--N--G!
FIRST COMES LOVE THEN COMES--
- EW, I DON'T WANNA KNOW
WHAT'S NEXT!