[IRENE]
It's over, Erza!
This is how you die!
[laughs]
[ERZA]
I can still move my right arm.
It's all or nothing!
At some point in time, people
started calling me Titania,
the named shared by
a legendary Fairy Queen.
Honestly, I've never
given that much thought
to what people chose to call me.
But if you're the
Queen of the Dragons...
...then I'll take the
name Titania with pride.
A queen who cherishes her
people and protects them.
I'll do all I can to
help those in need,
even if it ends
up destroying me!
Lend me your strength, Master!
Please!
[yelling]
Erza?
[yells]
[gasps]
[IRENE]
That's insane.
[yells]
[IRENE]
It's impossible!
[ERZA]
Get ready!
[IRENE] Maybe you can
cut through a meteor,
but you can't pierce
my dragon scales!
[IRENE]
Never!
[WENDY] I can enchant her sword
with Dragon Slayer magic.
[WENDY]
Enchant!
--[ERZA yells]
--[IRENE screams]
[yelling]
Hey. Y'okay?
[IRENE]
You've been a thorn in my side.
But that's all you are to me.
Your pathetic life ends here.
I'll see to that myself!
[gasps]
[BABY crying]
[IRENE sighs]
It's a girl.
I'm so relieved.
With her body,
I can live a new life.
It'll be easy.
Just enchant my
personality into her,
and I'll be free of this curse.
This wretched prison of flesh.
It's finally happening.
[IRENE] After 400 years,
I can be me again.
[IRENE] I'll have a body
without this Dragon Seed
growing inside of it.
Now, it's time for you
to be my vessel.
Stop.
Stop smiling.
Please.
I've endured 400 years
of pain and suffering.
I can't afford to hesitate.
[IRENE]
I've earned this chance.
And this child belongs to me.
[IRENE] I can do whatever
I want with her!
[IRENE gasps]
[IRENE]
Stop it.
Please! Stop smiling!
[IRENE]
Stop smiling!
[grunts]
[ERZA]
I smile....
...because there's
still fight in me!
Amazing.
[IRENE]
Too soft.
You don't know how
to finish a fight.
[ERZA]
My sword... it's gone.
[IRENE]
I have your blade.
Why?
[IRENE]
This is pathetic.
I'm the most powerful woman
in the empire, but still...
I can't go through with it.
I can't kill my daughter.
[ERZA]
But why?
Why? Good question.
[IRENE] I've tried to bury
the truth from myself.
I didn't enchant myself
into you back then...
...because I chose not to.
[IRENE]
You were so innocent.
So new.
And so beautiful.
[IRENE] Before I could change
my mind, I chose to abandon you.
[IRENE]
I'm not so naive
to think you'd believe
me after all I've done.
But your smile... reminded me...
[IRENE] Deep down, beneath
this cold shell, this mask...
Inside my heart...
I truly loved you.
[ERZA]
Farewell... mother.
[WENDY]
Erza?
Wendy.
Are you hurt?
I'm way more
worried about you.
Thank you, but... I think
I'm gonna be all right.
I mean, are you...
...are you okay emotionally?
[ERZA] Yeah, that was tough,
but I'll be fine.
You're sweet. Thank you.
[ERZA] Her life was full
of anger born from sorrow.
But the only parent
I've ever known...
...is our Master.
Actually, I've been wondering
about something for a bit.
Why can't I smell Master's scent
on the battlefield anymore?
There are a lot of other
scents all mixed together.
Maybe I just lost him somehow.
[ERZA]
It's okay, Wendy.
I'll always be here for you.
[WENDY]
He's... gone?
So... I'm dying?
Yes.
The Dragon Seed and
Demon Seed are merging.
Which means, your human
life is no more.
But I'm not ready.
There's so much for me to do.
This sucks.
I mean, I still gotta beat
Zeref and Acnologia.
Aw, man!
Hey! Why'd you do that?
I was already feelin' crappy!
[IGNEEL] I'm not done
talking, so listen closely.
[NATSU]
What is it?
[IGNEEL] Think about
what I just told you.
I clearly said that those
two seeds combining
would spell your death.
So don't let that happen.
You must choose
one or the other.
Choose one? But how?
By reflecting on yourself.
Deep inside, what are you?
[IGNEEL]
Are you a dragon...
...or a demon?
E.N.D. is my most powerful
creation. My legacy.
You'll face the same
choice as Igneel.
To let live or to kill.
Either way, I look
forward to it.
Am I a dragon? Or a demon?
I think you may have
found your answer.
Well?
I have.
I'm neither of 'em.
Because I'm human.
I'm Natsu Dragneel!
[IGNEEL]
Hm.
Yes.
I'm impressed, Natsu.
You found the right answer.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[IGNEEL] You were reborn
by a demon's power.
[IGNEEL] And you were raised
under a dragon's care.
But in your heart, you're human.
[IGNEEL] The struggle inside you
caused both seeds to grow,
each trying to take dominance.
Thanks, dad.
And now, you're ready
to move forward.
To walk on your own two feet.
I am.
[NATSU gasps]
[HAPPY, LUCY gasp]
Natsu!
You're alive!
You jerk!
Do you know how worried we were?
[HAPPY]
I was so scared.
I thought you would
never wake up again!
Is there a reason why
you're buck naked, Lucy?
I, uh... I can explain!
[PORLYUSICA]
You were as cold as the grave.
It was all she could do
to try and keep you warm.
[NATSU]
Granny!
You should be thanking
her right now.
I helped, too. I was
petting you the whole time.
You were?
Aw, buddy. Thanks!
Aye-aye, Sir!
Thanks, Lucy!
Of course. No big deal.
How are you feeling, Natsu?
I'm feelin' awesome.
All fired up!
That's great, but--
[NATSU]
Hm?
It's just... If you take
out Zeref, won't you--?
No way! You told her that?
[HAPPY]
Uh...
Don't worry, okay?
I'm gonna be fine.
Really.
A bunch of stuff
went on in my head,
and now, I made up my mind
that I'm human after all.
Boom! Problem solved.
[LUCY]
O-Okay, if you say so.
You know where
Gray and Erza are?
My memory's kinda fuzzy,
but I feel like I did
somethin' bad to 'em.
Gray's probably still
asleep in the next room.
And I think Erza is outside
fighting somewhere.
[ALL gasp]
What the--?
Hang on. We've seen
this light before.
Whoa!
This light.
Irene has fallen.
She must have.
The Universe One
spell is dissipating.
The world is going
back to how it was.
[WIZARDS chattering]
It's Magnolia!
Oh, wow!
It's back to normal again!
I think.
[LUCY]
Uh. Where are we?
We're at my place now?!
Seems perfect to me!
[NATSU] This is where
things usually start.
All we gotta do is
walk down the street...
...and head to Fairy Tail!
Aye, Sir!
[LUCY]
After Irene's defeat by Erza,
Magnolia finally goes back
to how it should be.
Mavis leads the
members of Fairy Tail
as they race to the guild hall,
with fire in all their bellies.
Meanwhile, the leader of
the Spriggan Twelve, August,
watches them from on high.
But just when order is
restored to the land,
calamity rains down.
Next Time: "Gray's Trump Card."
The end of Ragnarok
is drawing near.