- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Lucy: OUR SMALL GROUP OF
ALLIED GUILDS
TOOK ON THE ORACION SEIS.
AND TO MAKE THINGS
WAY MORE CONFUSING,
THEY RESURRECTED JELLAL!
- Wendy: I'M SORRY.
- Happy: ERZA GOT HURT,
HAD AN AMAZING RECOVERY,
THEN DISAPPEARED!
AND NIRVANA'S SEAL WAS BROKEN.
- Wendy: I'M SO SORRY, GUYS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
DEEP WITHIN THE WORTH WOODSEA,
ERZA AND JELLAL
WERE ONCE AGAIN REUNITED.
HOWEVER, JELLAL'S MEMORY
HAD BEEN WIPED CLEAN.
HE HAD NO KNOWLEDGE
OF HIS OWN DARK PAST.
TO PREVENT
AN EVEN DARKER FUTURE,
AND TO FREE ERZA
FROM THE BURDEN SHE CARRIED,
JELLAL DREW A MAGIC CIRCLE
DESIGNED TO DESTROY NIRVANA
AND HIMSELF WITH IT.
BUT ERZA HAS OTHER IDEAS.
- DON'T DO THIS!
- Cobra: IF HE GOES,
HE'S TAKIN' THE ONLY WAY
TO SHUT DOWN THAT SELF
DESTRUCTION CIRCLE WITH HIM.
- LISTEN TO ME.
YOU CAN'T!
I WON'T ALLOW YOU
TO DIE LIKE THIS.
YOU HAVE TO ATONE
FOR YOUR SINS!
IT MEANS NOTHING IF YOU DIE NOW,
IGNORANT OF WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
( sobbing )
OWN YOUR GUILT AND LIVE!
JELLAL!
- ( Happy speaking )
- ERZA, DON'T CRY.
THERE'S NO REASON TO.
YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
- JELLAL, YOU HAVE TO
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
- WHAT COULD BE THE MEANING
OF ALL THIS FOOLISHNESS?
- HE'S BACK.
- A MAGIC CIRCLE
OF SELF-DESTRUCTION.
- Cobra:
THIS IS JELLAL'S DOING!
WE'VE GONE THROUGH ALL THIS
TROUBLE TO BRING ABOUT NIRVANA,
AND THIS IDIOT
IS TRYING TO DESTROY IT.
- SPARE THE HYSTERICS.
I DON'T ANSWER TO THE NAME BRAIN
BY MERE CHANCE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW
I CAME TO BE CALLED THAT?
I ONCE WORKED AT THE BUREAU
OF MAGICAL DEVELOPMENT.
DURING MY TENURE THERE,
I PRODUCED HUNDREDS OF SPELLS,
INCLUDING THOSE DESIGNED TO
BRING DESTRUCTION,
SUCH AS THIS ONE.
I STILL HOLD THAT KNOWLEDGE
TO THIS VERY DAY.
IN FACT, I WAS THE ONE
WHO TAUGHT YOU HOW TO USE THEM.
OR HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN,
JELLAL?
THIS SPOT SHOULD SUFFICE.
FOCUS YOUR MIND,
YOUR ENERGY.
VISUALIZE THE DESTRUCTION
YOU WISH TO SEE AS A CLEAR,
CRYSTALLINE PATTERN
AND THEN MAKE IT SO.
- YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
- AND THIS,
AFTER A SINGLE LESSON?
YOUR SKILL IS OUTSTANDING.
I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU'VE MASTERED THE MAGIC CIRCLE
OF SELF-DESTRUCTION
IN RECORD TIME.
- I HAVEN'T "MASTERED" IT.
- WHAT?
- I NEED TO TAKE IT FURTHER,
TO A LEVEL OF DESTRUCTION
THAT ELIMINATES
EVERY TRACE OF EXISTENCE.
- THIS BOY.
SO IT SEEMS HE'S PLACED
HIMSELF UNDER ONE AS WELL.
HE INTENDS TO TAKE THE DISARM
CODE WITH HIM TO THE GRAVE,
DOES HE?
- I DON'T THINK HE'S GONNA BE
TRAVELING DOWN
MEMORY LANE WITH YOU, BRAIN.
SORRY, BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THAT
ETHER-NANO WIPED IT ALL OUT.
- ( laughs )
IS THAT SO?
HOW COMICAL.
WE HAVE NO FURTHER NEED
OF HIS ASSISTANCE.
I KNOW HOW TO NULLIFY
THIS MAGIC CIRCLE,
QUITE SIMPLY.
- NO!
- YOU CAN'T.
- WHOA!
- ( laughs )
YOU TRIED YOUR BEST, JELLAL.
BUT NOW NIRVANA
IS FINALLY UNDER MY CONTROL!
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT!
- NIRVANA, ARISE!
- ERZA!
- REVEAL YOUR TRUE FACE!
- YEAH!
I HEAR IT.
THE SOUND OF THE FUTURE,
OF LIGHT
CRASHING TO THE GROUND!
- NO!  JELLAL!
- ERZA!
- I THINK IT'S GETTING WORSE.
- QUICKLY, CHILD,
LET'S GET TO SAFETY.
- NO, IT CAN'T BE.
IT'S CHANGED.
- I'M AFRAID
THAT YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
IT'S ENTERING THE FINAL STAGE.
NIRVANA'S RESURRECTION!
- MAN!
- WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
- SO OUR MISSION
WAS A FAILURE.
- NO WAY!
- HOPE THAT'S NOT AS BAD
AS IT LOOKS.
- YEAH, I'M PRETTY SURE IT IS.
- Gray: AND ONCE AGAIN,
ERZA IS RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF IT.
- SERIOUSLY?
- Natsu: THIS IS THE MOST
DANGEROUS THING
I'VE EVER SMELLED.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW?
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
- SOMETHING
UNBELIEVABLY MASSIVE.
OH YEAH.
- CAN YOU MAKE OUT WHAT EXACTLY?
- ( all shouting )
- Natsu: AW GREAT,
NOW WHAT'S GOING ON?!
- Gray: I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT IT'S EVERYWHERE.
- Lucy:
DO YOU THINK THIS IS NIRVANA?
- Lyon: IT DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE MAGIC TO ME.
- Natsu:
WHY IS EVERYTHING SHAKING?!
- Gray: GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF,
MAN.
- Lucy: HERE COMES
THAT REALLY BAD FEELING AGAIN.
- Lyon: YOU SAID IT.
- Lucy: WHAT DID I TELL YOU?!
- ( all shouting )
- YOU COWARDS!
YOU NEVER LEAVE A MAN BEHIND!
- ( screaming )
CARLA!
- DON'T WORRY, I'VE GOT YOU.
- THANKS.
LOOK OVER THERE!
- WHAT IS IT?
COULD THAT BE NIRVANA?
- YES!
AT LONG LAST
I HAVE OBTAINED IT.
THE ULTIMATE WEAPON
WHICH EXTINGUISHES LIGHT.
THE LEGENDARY REVERSAL MAGIC--
NIRVANA.
THOSE NEAR-SIGHTED GUILDS
WILL CLING TO THEIR PIETY,
THEIR FELLOWSHIP, AND TRUST.
BUT NOW, SUCH THINGS
WILL BE STRIPPED OF MEANING.
- ERZA.
- THE MAGIC CIRCLE
YOU PLACED ON YOURSELF,
YOU MUST UNDO IT
THIS INSTANT.
YOU HAVE A DUTY
TO STAY ALIVE.
- I FAILED.
I WASN'T ABLE TO
PUT A STOP TO NIRVANA.
NOW THE WORLD IS DOOMED.
- NO, THERE'S ALWAYS HOPE.
LOOK THERE.
- AAH!
- Lyon: ALL RIGHT, FAIRY TAIL,
IF ANYBODY CAN DO IT,
IT'S YOU.
- HEY, CARLA,
WE SHOULD GO UP THERE TOO
AND TRY TO HELP 'EM OUT.
- AGREED.
- LET'S LEND THEM A HAND.
- YOU SHOULD START
BY TAKING MINE.
- THANK YOU.
- HELPING OUT A FELLOW MAN
IN NEED.
THIS IS BROTHERLY LOVE.
OH YEAH!
- YOU SEE, AS LONG AS WE
DRAW BREATH INTO OUR LUNGS,
WE SHALL KEEP HOPE ALIVE
INSIDE OUR HEARTS.
- ONCE I GET TO THE TOP,
I'LL PUNCH THIS THING
INTO A BILLION PIECES!
- SO WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH YOU GUYS MATCHING OUTFITS?
- NOW IS NOT THE TIME!
- AND THAT HOPE WILL GUIDE YOU
THROUGHOUT YOUR LIFE.
SO LIVE.
- I WILL.
NOW LET'S GO.
- YES.
- ( grunting )
MAN.
WHAT A REVOLTING DEVELOPMENT!
WHERE DID THOSE JUVENILE
SNOT-NOSED PUNKS RUN OFF TO?
FOR THAT MATTER, WHERE AM I?!
THIS IS NO WAY
TO TREAT A MAN!
- ( all screaming )
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDIN' ME.
COME ON!
WHAT'S WITH YOU?
YOU CAN'T START
GETTING SICK RIGHT NOW.
- I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
- JUST TRY.
- THIS THING'S MOVING
FROM ONE PLACE TO ANOTHER.
- IT MAY BE MOVING, BUT IT'S
NOT LIKE IT'S A VEHICLE.
DON'T THINK OF IT THAT WAY.
- ( growling )
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT!
( grunting )
( whimpering )
MY TUMMY HURTS.
- JUST THINK OF IT
LIKE A GIANT OCTOPUS.
BEING ON THE BACK OF AN ANIMAL
DOESN'T BOTHER YOU, DOES IT?
- AN OCTOPUS IN THE WOODS
IS ALL KINDS OF WRONG.
- DON'T SWEAT THE WEIRD DETAILS.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. I JUST GOTTA
GET MY MIND AT EASE.
- WATCH OUT!
- YOU IDIOT!  STAY ALERT, MAN.
- I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
THIS IS A PIECE OF CAKE.
( grunting )
( whimpering, screaming )
- NATSU!
- AAH!
GOOD WORK, PAL!
- AYE, SIR.
- GREAT TIMING.
AWESOME CATCH.
- THAT STUPID HOTHEAD
NEARLY GAVE ME A HEART ATTACK.
- WOW, HAPPY,
THAT WAS TOTALLY AWESOME!
YOU'RE MY HERO.
- NOW ISN'T THIS BETTER?
FEELS PRETTY AMAZING TO RIDE THE
WIND LIKE THIS, DON'T YA THINK?
- YEAH.
WAY BETTER.
- TAKE IT ALL THE WAY
TO THE TOP, GUYS.
WE'RE GONNA
HEAD THROUGH THERE
AND CHECK OUT WHAT THINGS
ARE LIKE ON THE INSIDE.
- RIGHT!
- AYE, SIR.
- OH WEIRD.
- Happy: YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE
SOME KIND OF CREEPY OLD CITY.
- Natsu: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT SMELL.
I CAN SMELL HIM.
- YOU ACTUALLY
PULLED THIS THING OFF.
YOU GOT US NIRVANA.
- ( chuckles )
- A CITY THAT'S BEEN LONG DEAD
BROUGHT BACK TO LIFE.
CUBELLIOS, DON'T YOU
THINK THAT'S AMAZING?
- ( hisses )
- BEHOLD, COBRA.
LOOK AT THE WORLD THAT NOW
SPREADS OUT BENEATH OUR FEET.
AN ENTIRE CITY,
UNSHACKLED FROM TIME
AND THE EARTH ITSELF.
THIS IS NIRVANA'S TRUE FORM.
AND FROM THIS SEAT OF POWER,
I CAN MOVE THIS CITY
TO ANYWHERE I SEE FIT.
- OH YEAH?
WELL, I'M SURE
YOU GOT SOMEWHERE IN MIND.
SO WHERE WE GOIN'?
- I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT OUR FIRST TARGET SHALL BE.
A CERTAIN GUILD HALL.
- SO WE'RE STARTING
WITH A BANG, ARE WE?
- IT SHALL BE THE FIRST OF
MANY LIGHTS TO BE EXTINGUISHED.
NIRVANA!
BEGIN YOUR MARCH NOW.
TRANSFORM MY DARKNESS
INTO LIGHT!
- AAH!
I'M PUTTING THE BRAKES
ON THIS THING.
- NO, THE FIRE DRAGON!
- ( Happy grunting )
- FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- STOP THIS FLAMING IDIOT
AT ONCE, COBRA.
- I HEAR YA.
CUBELLIOS!
- AAH!
THAT DOES IT!
I'M FIRED UP NOW.
AAH!
NICE SAVE.
THANKS, PAL.
- AYE.
- OKAY.
AAH!
- THAT ISN'T RIGHT.
EVERYONE KNOWS SNAKES
AREN'T SUPPOSED TO FLY.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
I THOUGHT VEHICLES MADE YOU
MOTION SICK OR SOMETHING?
SO YOU SHOULD BE PUKING
YOUR GUTS OUT RIGHT NOW.
- HAPPY'S NOT A VEHICLE!
HE'S MY FRIEND.
YOU TELL HIM, NATSU!
- I GET IT.
SO YOU GOTTA STAY UP HERE
IN THE AIR,
'CAUSE BEING ON NIRVANA
WHILE IT'S MOVING
IS GONNA MAKE YOU THROW UP.
THAT'S THE DUMBEST THING
I EVER HEARD.
- YEAH,
WELL, IT MAKES SENSE TO ME.
AND BESIDES, I'M GONNA STOP
THIS OVERSIZED PIECE OF JUNK.
- YOU'RE GONNA NEED
THE DEVIL'S LUCK TO DO THAT.
'CAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'RE GONNA GET NEAR BRAIN.
- BRAIN?
IS THAT GUY
THE ONE DRIVING THIS THING?
- BRING IT ON,
FIRE DRAGON SLAYER!
- YOU GOT IT!
I'M COMING RIGHT FOR YA,
BUDDY!
PSYCHE!
STRAIGHT FOR THE BRAIN!
- AYE.
- ( both screaming )
- WELL, THAT CERTAINLY DIDN'T
WORK OUT THE WAY I WANTED IT TO.
- IT'S LIKE HE KNEW
WHAT WE WERE GONNA DO.
- I CAN "HEAR" YOUR MOVEMENTS
BEFORE YOU MAKE THEM.
- SAY WHAT?
- OH YEAH.
LOUD AND CLEAR.
SO LET'S HAVE SOME FUN.
- ( panting )
- I'M SORRY THAT WAS SO HARD.
I WISH I COULD HELP OUT MORE.
- IT'S NO MATTER, CHILD.
WE'RE HERE,
AND IN ONE PIECE, MOSTLY.
BUT NOW THAT WE'VE ARRIVED,
EXACTLY WHAT IS IT
YOU PLAN TO DO?
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIND JELLAL
UP HERE, AREN'T YOU?
- I'M NOT!
- TRUTHFULLY.
- BUT, WELL, IN A WAY,
I GUESS I AM, SORT OF.
BUT THIS THING
DOES HAVE TO BE STOPPED.
SO NOW THAT I'M HERE,
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
I CAN DO TO MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
- MAYBE.
- ( giggles )
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I COULD BE WRONG.
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
IT'S GOING WHERE I THINK IT IS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHERE DO YOU THINK IT'S GOING?
- IF IT CONTINUES TO TRAVEL
ON THE SAME COURSE IT IS NOW,
THEN VERY SOON, IT'LL TRAMPLE
RIGHT OVER THE HOME
OF THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD.
- MAN, I CAN'T SEEM TO LAND
A SINGLE HIT ON THIS JOKER.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS ON WHAT
KIND OF MAGIC HE MIGHT BE USING?
- ALL I KNOW IS WE BETTER
BEAT HIM REALLY QUICKLY.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A CHANCE AT THE BOSS.
SO ARE YOU READY?
IT'S TIME TO GIVE THESE GUYS
A BEAT-DOWN
AND STOP THIS HUNK OF JUNK
IN ITS TRACKS. - AYE.
- THIS OUGHTA BE A RIOT.
A GREAT WAY
TO KEEP ME ENTERTAINED
WHILE WE MAKE THE TRIP
OVER TO OUR NEXT STOP.
COME ON,
LET'S GET THIS FIGHT STARTED.
- Natsu: YOU GOT IT!
I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: HOLD ON A SECOND.
HOW COME THAT SNAKE
GETS TO HAVE WINGS
AND FLY AROUND LIKE ME?
CAN I SUE
FOR COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT?
- Natsu: I DON'T KNOW.
DO I LOOK LIKE A LAWYER
TO YOU?
- OKAY, FINE.
THEN JUST BEAT IT UP.
TEACH IT A LESSON
FOR COPYING ME.
- WHAT ABOUT CARLA?
SHE'S TOTALLY
COPYING YOU TOO, MAN.
- YEAH, MAYBE,
BUT IT'S CUTE WHEN SHE DOES IT.
- Both: NEXT TIME--
"SUPER AERIAL BATTLE: NATSU
VERSUS COBRA"!
- Natsu: THAT SNAKE
IS TOTALLY COOL THOUGH.
AND IT HAS POISON.
- WELL, I GOT TONS OF FISH.
- SO WHAT?
HOW IS THAT COOL?