[WARROD]
There it is!
[MAVIS]
This story takes place in a time
before Fairy Tail's existence.
A harsher time.
It's about a girl
with a silly dream,
fighting despair and anguish
with nothing but the
heart they stab at.
It's a tale of overcoming.
Of chasing hope.
Of friends who formed a guild.
Is that the enormous old church
you were telling me about?
[PRECHT] Kardia Cathedral
is one of Fiore's
three largest churches.
The legends say that long ago,
the angel known
as St. Mikardia--
Hey, look! See that?
What the heck?
[PRECHT]
What is that?
[YURI] It's gotta be
Kardia cathedral, but--
Why's there a
blue-skulled dragon?
What the hell's going on?
[PRECHT] That dragon
skeleton is definitely
not supposed to be there.
The town looks
pretty torn up, too.
[YURI]
Yeah, that's an understatement.
[WARROD]
And there's not a soul in sight.
I know who is here.
The Blue Skull guild.
You okay?
So do we really have to sneak
around like a bunch of thieves?
Well, we did come here to steal.
Blue Skull has the Tenrou Orb,
and we're taking it from them.
We can't risk being
seen by anyone.
It could blow the
entire mission.
So we gotta stay hidden
for a just little while.
At least until we
find their base.
Okay, fine.
But we all saw that blue
skeleton on top of the church.
Don't ya think that means
they're probably inside of it?
[PRECHT] That's not enough
information to act upon.
They might have other
hideouts around here.
The Tenrou Orb could be
somewhere else.
We have to be sure.
What do you think, Mavis?
Uh. Where did she go?
[PRECHT]
Despite her history,
it seems she's not
the kind to wait.
[rustling]
[BOTH gasp]
Oh. Ha. They nearly
scared me to death.
The natural energy of
this place feels good.
[ZERA]
Mhm.
But still, the city gives
off a really bad vibe.
Like something evil is there.
[BOTH gasp]
Wait! What's wrong?
Hey, guys.
Do you think that she's found
Blue Skull's hideout already?
Come on, you've gotta
check this out!
Hush! We're trying to
be sneaky, remember?
Isn't it amazing?
What?
I must be missing something here
because all I see is a
giant puddle of water.
You don't see how
beautiful it is?
There is something
about this place.
The way the trees and the water
feel, it's kinda magical.
Definitely a peaceful spot,
that's for sure.
Can the rest of you feel
the incredible energy
filling the place?
Huh.
Now that you mention it,
just standing here and
enjoying the scenery
is invigorating
in some weird way.
Yeah!
All right then.
What do you say we set up our
home base right in this spot?
That sounds wonderful!
[ZERA]
Let's do it!
[MAVIS chuckles]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[WIZARD A] You can run,
but ya can't hide!
[WIZARDS laughing]
[YURI]
Mavis!
And there she goes again.
Aw, man, why does she
have to be such a pain?
[WIZARDS chuckling]
[BOTH scream]
That's a bull's-eye!
[WIZARD laughing]
What's going on?
You see that emblem?
They're from Blue Skull.
Really?
It ain't as much fun if ya just
stand there, so get movin'!
[MAKO]
Please, listen to me.
If killing is the only
thing that'll satisfy you,
then you can kill me.
But I beg you, please
spare my daughter's life!
[MIKO]
Mommy!
Okay, that sounds like
a fair deal to me.
We'll kill you before we
take out the little brat.
[rumbling]
[WIZARDS scream]
[roars]
[ALL scream]
[WIZARD A]
Crap!
[WIZARD B]
Run!
We've gotta get
out of here, okay?
[MAVIS]
Don't worry. It's safe now.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIKO]
Mommy?
[MAKO]
Wait, how can you say that?
You saw that giant
beast, didn't you?
As a matter of fact,
that "giant beast" was
my very own guardian.
Actually, it's just an illusion
I created to scare them.
[MIKO]
It's gone.
So are those Blue Skull punks.
And once again, I'm impressed.
Her illusions are
extremely life-like.
Here ya go.
My name is Mavis. Are you okay?
Yeah. Thank you.
You saved our lives just now.
I don't know how to repay you.
[YURI] Well, you can start by
sharing some info with us.
About what?
[PRECHT]
The Blue Skull guild.
I'll tell you everything
I know about them.
But they're gonna be back soon.
We need to go somewhere to talk.
Is this your place?
Doesn't look like you're
still in business.
Not anymore.
I know this is probably
hard for you to believe,
but Magnolia was once
a thriving city.
There were always lots
of people out and about.
And the streets were lined
with shops and cafes.
Folks from all over
the area would come here
to take in the sights.
During the harvest festival,
there would be thousands
of them here to celebrate.
But that Magnolia seems like
a distant memory these days.
The few people that
remain live in fear.
Blue Skull. They caused
all of this, didn't they?
Yeah.
It was so peaceful,
until the day they came
from out of nowhere.
[MAKO]
I'll never forget it.
So many people lost
their lives that day.
We were just ordinary folk
with no way to defend
ourselves against them.
In a matter of hours, the city
was under their control.
They seized all of the supplies
of food and medicine.
We had nothing after that.
And then they levied heavy taxes
that were impossible to pay.
The price for non-payment
was very steep.
If you were lucky,
they might let you live.
But they were ruthless.
Anyone that showed
any sign of resisting
was killed as an example,
right before our eyes.
No.
Does that mean that they
murdered your husband as well?
[MAKO]
They did.
That's just like us.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
[MIKO] You see?
Daddy made me that bread.
It was special for my birthday!
What? Is that really bread?
Quiet.
That's a super cute present.
Yeah, and it was
super yummy too!
He was really good at
makin' stuff like that!
He would always make
me special bread
to give me on my birthdays
in all kinds'a shapes.
He'd make 'em into animals,
and sometimes he'd make 'em
look like trees and flowers.
Yum. Hearing about it
is makin' me kinda hungry.
This year, I was gonna
make one for my daddy.
I wanted to give him a really
good one for his birthday,
but he was gone
before I could do it.
[MIKO crying]
Blue Skull is even bigger than
they were when they attacked us.
They were a small
force, but strong.
And now there must be
hundreds upon hundreds
of members in the guild.
That is quite troubling.
[MAKO]
You're travelers, aren't you?
My advice is to leave
and get as far away from
Magnolia as you can.
[MIKO]
Wait!
[gasps]
What is it, Miko?
Thank you.
For saving me and Mommy earlier.
So here! I want you
to have this!
That's such a cute and
thoughtful thing to do.
Thank you.
[giggles]
What do we do?
[PRECHT]
About what?
Don't play dumb with me.
What're we gonna do
about Blue Skull?
I don't know. With that many
members, what can we do?
You okay?
[PRECHT] Don't forget,
we're only here to get the orb.
Nothing more.
Yeah, I know.
Well, although I feel bad
for Miko and her mom,
you hit the nail
right on the head.
We just came here to nab
an S-class treasure.
Taking down Blue Skull is
definitely not on the agenda.
Yep, you're right about that.
Wait, Seriously?
You're just gonna let all of
these people keep suffering?
We can't do anything
to help them!
I don't understand how anyone
can see what's happening
here and just walk away!
So you're just a bunch of
heartless cowards after all.
We can't just take
on a wizard guild.
Especially not such
a massive one.
Your illusions just
aren't gonna cut it.
We don't have any real way to
fight against magic users.
But they need us.
[OLD MAN A]
Excuse me, are you travelers?
There's nothing left in
this place but heartache.
Leave if you value your lives.
That's not an option.
We have some things to
do before we can go.
[PRECHT]
Sir, if you don't mind,
we'd like to ask
you some questions.
There're no answers here, sorry.
But this once
great city is dying.
Is there no hope for it?
No, none. Death has
taken hold of this city.
The day Blue Skull arrived
here, we were doomed.
[screams]
[BOTH gasp]
Is there no hope for it?
No, none. Death has
taken hold of this city.
The day Blue Skull arrived
here, we were doomed.
[screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[PRECHT]
Sir!
[YURI]
Hey!
Whoa! What just happened?
It was a magic bullet!
Who would do such a thing?
Based on the
attack's trajectory,
it came from up there!
Aw, yeah! Perfect shot!
[WIZARD E laughs]
Down like a dusty old
sack of potatoes!
All right! Now watch me
take this kid out next!
Those bastards!
[PRECHT]
Indeed.
[WIZARDS laughing]
You lost?
Because there's no way
you came here on purpose
unless you were lookin' to die.
[WIZARD E laughs]
Good night!
Oh, no!
That bun was a very
special gift to me!
Why in the hell should I care?
But you're goin' down
this time, ya little brat!
You wouldn't dare.
[WIZARD E laughs]
Seein' that bread reminds
me of that baker guy
we roasted a while back.
Roasted?
I think you meant to say
we toasted him, right?
These are the same people
who murdered Miko's father?
Let's make them pay!
[PRECHT]
And dearly!
Now! Yuri! Warrod!
Okay!
Yeah!
They're just killers.
They don't give a damn
about human life.
Everybody I cared about
is dead because of them.
My father. My friends
from school!
I know.
Uh-oh. You losers are
gonna make us pay, are ya?
You think you can just walk into
our town and challenge us?
Well, think again!
Bring it on!
Crystal bomb!
That's right!
You're definitely gonna pay for
what you did to little Miko!
If you like magic
bullets so much,
why don't I give you a whole
mouth full of 'em, huh?
[WIZARD E screams]
[YURI]
Heh.
You guys are pathetic.
Is this the best wizards can do?
[yelps]
[WIZARD G]
What's going on here?!
[WIZARD H] Some foreigners
are on a rampage!
[WIZARD I]
What? On our turf?
Here comes backup.
Don't you worry, I know
exactly what to do.
[YURI]
Mavis!
Now come forth.
Tenrou Soldiers!
[WIZARDS gasping]
What the--?
Whoa! Where did they come from?
Dunno!
There's so many!
[WIZARD H] It's like they
came outta thin air!
Crazy!
No way! There's too many!
Is it some kinda invading army?
Or did she summon them?
Let me speak to your master,
and I'll keep them at bay.
So what do we do?
[MAVIS]
Call him here now!
[GEOFFREY]
But I'm already here.
[gasps]
Master Geoffrey?
I came to see for myself
what this fuss is about.
That's the guy! Let's go
pound his ugly face in!
[PRECHT]
Quiet, Yuri.
So he's the one in charge.
We're here to take
back what you stole
from Tenrou Island
seven years ago.
My people's sacred artifact,
called the Tenrou Orb.
[GEOFFREY]
Hmph.
But if you refuse
to return it...
[GEOFFREY] Please. Tell me
what happens if I refuse.
Then they will attack.
Oh, is that so. Hmm...
[GEOFFREY]
Kill them all.
[WIZARD G]
What? But, Master--
[WIZARD H]
We're completely outnumbered!
Surely we can defeat illusions.
[gasps]
This is bad.
She was tryin' to fool us!
All right! Crush 'em, men!
[WIZARDS yelling]
Aw, crap!
[PRECHT]
Fall back!
[WARROD, YURI]
Let's go!
They've got us surrounded!
We're just gonna have
to bust through 'em!
[BOTH yelling]
Hey! Come on!
Zera.
We have to get out
of here. Let's go!
Yeah.
[WIZARDS snickering]
Got a special delivery
just for you!
[gasps]
[screams]
[WIZARDS lauging]
You shouldn't tangle
with wizards.
[PRECHT]
Yuri!
He got hit!
No.
Let's light this joker up, boys!
Oh, no, Precht!
[WARROD]
Precht! Yuri!
Damn it!
Blast 'em!
You're not killin' anyone else!
Especially not my friends!
Mavis!
Right!
They're gettin' away!
What are ya standin'
around for? After 'em!
That's enough.
The terror they just experienced
will keep them away for good.
[MAVIS] We may've had to turn
tail and run that day,
but we were heading straight
towards a new beginning.
Little did we know; he was
waiting in that forest.
And he would change
our lives forever.
[MAVIS] After a humbling defeat
at the hands of Blue Skull,
we sought shelter in the
forest west of Magnolia.
My overconfidence put my
friends' lives at risk.
As I reflected on my failure,
I encountered a lone wizard
trying to escape
civilization in the woods.
This fateful meeting would
change my life forever,
and directly lead to the
founding of Fairy Tail.
Next Time: "Conveyer of Magic."
Light and darkness
gently intertwine.