[Citizens reacting in fear]
[NATSU] Outta my
way, Michelle!
Don't you dare come
any closer to my big sister!
Let this be a warning to you.
If you don't leave us alone I'll
be forced to take your lives.
[NATSU] Don't threaten us!
Geez, first you
trick us and now this?
You're not the man
that I thought you were.
Let Lucy go this instant!
You guys.
Michelle, please!
[IMITATIA]
Don't worry, Big Sister.
I swear to you.
I will keep you safe.
No way!
She's coming with us!
Me and Elfman will try
and keep her distracted
while you go up there and
work on getting Lucy free.
[ELFMAN] You got it!
[COCO] You got it!
Let's go!
♪
[WAKABA] Our poor,
old master is workin' overtime
in order to protect us
from the Real Nightmare.
Shame our new master
couldn't handle it.
If you think that
I'm incompetent then
just come right
out and say it!
Would ya quit takin'
everything personally?
[MACAO] Any word on Kinana?
[WAKABA] Nope.
Fried's Enchantments should
last for a few more hours,
but they haven't even
picked up her trail yet.
[MACAO] Damn.
What now?
I wish that there was
some way I could help out.
Just relax, as master you
need to stay calm and collected.
This might not help, but I
haven't seen Romeo in a while.
Well, I guess it's about time I
stop calling him my little boy.
Why?
'Cause, whether I like it or
not, he's grown into a man now.
[MACAO] And it seems like
he's takin' after dear old dad.
[ROMEO] Whoa.
[ROMEO] Hang on! I'm comin'
for ya Natsu and Lucy!
Michelle.
[HAPPY] Angel Tears!
[ELFMAN] Fight me like a man!
Hey, are you
guys alright?
[COCO] That's eight points!
Uh yeah, we're okay!
[ELFMAN] You've
gotta be careful, Natsu!
She'll aim for your
vitals with deadly accuracy!
[ELFMAN] Remember,
she took you down with one hit!
Ya don't have
to remind me.
[IMITATIA] I find human
bodies so interesting.
[IMITATIA] No matter how
brawny they are all it takes
is one strike to
their vital organs and
they'll be incapacitated
by intense pain.
What's with you?
You're nothin' like the ditzy,
crybaby who we used to know.
[IMITATIA] That was just an
act to infiltrate your guild.
[IMITATIA] As I told you before,
my name is Imitatia.
I'm a member of
the Neo-Oración Seis.
[ELFMAN] How could you?
I'll make you pay!
I can cause someone
intense pain too, y'know!
How do ya like that?
[COCO] You're
really stuck in there!
[IMITATIA] It's no use.
You can attack all you want,
but my body doesn't feel pain.
There's absolutely
nothing you can do
to make me forget my purpose.
In other words,
I won't be fazed by
ridiculous human emotions.
[NATSU]
If they're so ridiculous,
then how do you explain
that look in your eye?
[IMITATIA] What look?
Don't play dumb with me.
People who fight
for something that
they believe in,
even the bad guys,
always have some kinda
brightness in their eyes.
It's different than that "spaced
out" look you've got now.
How would you know?
Makin' any progress
up there, Coco?
[COCO] I'm pulling
but she won't budge!
You're trying to confuse me,
but my heart is unwavering.
I'm doing this
for my big sister!
[NATSU] Is that so?
Ain't that a coincidence,
the same goes for us!
[NATSU] Y'know Happy's got
a theory and if he's right,
we've gotta defeat you if we
wanna be able to save Lucy.
So guess what?
You're goin' down, ya phony!
Let's do this!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Roar!
[ELFMAN] Manly attack!
[IMITATIA] Heat doesn't faze me!
[ELFMAN] Manly Take Over!
Belcusas!
[ELFMAN] What in the--?
What's she doin' to me?
A shock from my Cilice will
bring about debilitating pain!
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon Brilliant Flame!
[COCO] I can't believe
you'd betray your sister...
Just for a stupid mission?
What mission?
Coco!
[IMITATIA] I couldn't
care less about the orders
I am given, or fulfilling
meaningless tasks.
I follow my heart
and nothing more.
It may be filled
with pain and sorrow,
but that heartache is what
compels me to fight.
Magic is
all about heart.
And the power of my
determination is second to none.
[PANTHERLILY] Any luck?
[HAPPY] No, I've
looked all over,
but there's no sign of
Samuel anywhere.
[HAPPY] I'm worried he's
gonna find Lucy before we do!
[PANTHERLILY] Calm down.
She won't be that easy to
find in a giant place like this.
I understand that
the Legion Platoon is just
trying to stop the
Infinity Clock like we are.
But why hurt Lucy?
[PANTHERLILY] After assessing
the facts, do you honestly
believe this is the best
way to stop it, Sammy?
[PANTHERLILY] He thinks
he's doing the right thing.
Even though we may not agree.
To him it's what must be done.
Well, if you're
his brother,
then why don't you just
tell him that he's wrong?
[PANTHERLILY] I'm not
really his brother, numbskull!
[SAMUEL] This isn't
about duty or calculations.
And it has nothing to do
with Exceeds or humans,
guilds or churches.
[SAMUEL] This is about
fighting for what I believe in.
And that is the doctrine
I was raised on.
Therefore, I'm afraid
I have no other choice.
Forgive me, Brother.
[JEAN-LUC]
We've done it, everyone!
We've actually
finished deciphering it!
[MACAO] Really?
So tell us, how do we go about
stopping the Real Nightmare?
The only way to do
that is to terminate
the Infinity Clock's ownership.
Basically, the seals branded
on it must be removed.
I bet Happy's gonna
be thrilled when
he finds out that he was right!
This definitely
supports his theory.
Guess the 'lil guy's
a lot smarter than he looks.
We know Grim Reaper
and Racer have fallen so far.
That means there's four left.
If we can defeat them,
then we'll be able to save Lulu!
Now that we
know what to do,
I say it's time for
us to take action!
[LEVY] Natsu and
the others have got this.
[MAKAROV] I'm confident they'll
defeat the Neo-Oración Seis.
[COBRA] Nice try but I'm afraid
you're outta luck, Titania.
My ultra-shock
waves can instantly
obliterate even the
strongest of blades.
[ERZA] Can you still
hear what I'm thinking?
All I can hear right now is
that you think you can beat me.
Yes, and that is all
you're going to
hear until I've succeeded.
[COBRA] Now I hear your
desperation as you try to think
up a way to overpower me,
and that strong will
of yours refusing
to give up the fight.
[ERZA] It seems your favorite
sound is that of your own voice.
Your magic doesn't frighten me.
I can hear thoughts as well.
[COBRA] Is that so?
I can hear the
thoughts of my friends.
They're saying
they refuse to lose
and that I shouldn't
give in either.
[COBRA] I hate to break it to
you but those are your thoughts.
You're so desperate
to win that your mind
is starting to play
tricks on you.
[ERZA] You wouldn't understand.
You're wrong.
I know they belong to my friends
because they are always with me.
Their love and friendship
is the source of my strength.
It drives me.
You have friends, don't you?
Can't you hear
them in your heart?
[COBRA] I'll warn you, the more
you talk, the angrier I get.
[COBRA] You're a
stubborn one, aren't you?
[ERZA] I know what you went
through in the Tower of Heaven,
I suffered the same
pain and anguish as you.
What I don't understand
is why you'd want
anybody else to
suffer the same way!
[COBRA] Are you referring
to Real Nightmare?
I honestly don't care
what happens with it.
Talk about making others suffer,
here you are yammering on
about all of your comrades.
When I've lost the
only friend I've had.
I knew you were
hiding something from me.
Step out of the shadows
and into the light.
It's the only way
to free yourself
from the pain you're feeling!
[COBRA] Step out of the
shadows and into the light?
There's no way that
you could understand.
[GRAY] So there's
only four left, huh?
Well, I'm about to
make it three.
[ANGEL] Why did
you take your shirt off?
You gave me a good thrashin'
before but not this time!
You'll be a real angel
when I'm done!
Oh, how I
hate stubborn men.
[GRAY] Beatin' up girls
'ain't really my thing,
but I gotta do this
to save my friend!
This one's for Lucy!
[LUCY] What is this?
What's happening to me?
Where am I?
[WARREN] Alright, thanks
for keeping us up to date!
It's really good to know
that Happy's theory was right!
And if we defeat all
of the Neo-Oración Seis
their seals will disappear
from the Infinity Clock.
[CARLA] That means they'll
completely lose ownership of it
and with nobody left
to control the clock,
the Real Nightmare is
bound to disappear as well!
[WENDY] But what about Lucy?
[WARREN]
Jean-Luc thinks she'll be freed
as soon as the all
of the seals are gone.
[WENDY] I don't know why,
but it feels like the
sky is getting restless.
[CARLA] I agree.
Do you think it's
possible that the
effects of the Real Nightmare
have been weakened
because two of the
six seals on the Infinity Clock
have disappeared?
I hope so, but
I'm a little afraid that
the clock will try
to protect the seals.
[SHAMSIEL] Hello there!
How's it goin?
[GRAY] Aw man,
not you again!
Ice Geyser!
[SHAMSIEL] An angel's light
is like a thousand suns.
See for yourself!
[SHAMSIEL] Huh?
[GRAY] That was just a decoy!
Ice Make: Death Scythe!
Curse you.
[GRAY] Looks like
I sent that evil chubster
you call an "angel"
back to Heaven.
[ANGEL]
That's right, back to Heaven.
Go on! I want
you to impale me.
Say what?
Have you gone insane?
[ANGEL] I want to vanish
into the sky like an angel.
I want it more than
anything in the world.
[GRAY] What?
[ANGEL] Please, I'm begging
you, send me into the
sky with Shamsiel.
It's my wish.
I want to be among the angels.
When you make
my wish come true,
this will truly
be a Death Scythe.
[GRAY] What the
hell has gotten into you?
What's wrong,
why can't you do it?
No. I could but
I don't wanna.
[ANGEL] If you're not
going to grant my wish,
then I'll have to destroy you!
[ANGEL] Cost, thirty!
I summon Baraqiel!
[GRAY] Geez! It's one after
another with this chick!
[GRAY] You're not
a freakin' angel!
You're a human and you know it!
[ANGEL] Time's up.
[GRAY] Oh crap!
[explosion]
[GRAY] No way!
[DAN] All right everyone,
let's calm down.
Dan Straight of the
Legion Platoon is here!
[ANGEL] Great, not you again.
[DAN] At long last,
I have found you, my Angie.
You can play hard to get
but I will win you over.
My love.
You can't run forever.
Hurry and dispose
of him, Baraqiel.
[DAN] Watch it, buddy!
Didn't anybody ever tell you not
to come between two lovers?
Okay, scram!
You've had plenty of alone
time with my Angiepoo.
It's only fair that I get
some too, dontcha think?
But you don't
even know what's
going on, I mean,
what about Lucy?
[DAN] I'm sure that
Natsu and Coco will figure
out a way to help my ex somehow.
[GRAY] So now she's your ex?
[DAN] I just had a chat
with Gray and he's cool with us
runnin' off and startin'
our new lives together!
[ANGEL] That's the
last thing I want.
This is the beginning of
our "happily ever after", Angie!
C'mon!
Our honeymoon awaits!
[ANGEL] You disgust me!
[GRAY] Talk about
divine intervention.
You're vulgar, distasteful,
and a complete waste of breath!
She's playin' coy.
Just watch, she'll come
runnin' any moment now.
[GRAY] You really that clueless?
[ANGEL] For the cost of one
hundred I ask that you come
forth from the light,
and obliterate in my name!
[ANGEL] I summon
the angel who
plays the sound
of the end times.
Raguel!
[DAN] Keep blowin'!
I won't back down!
[DAN] I'm willing to risk
my life for you, Angie!
[ANGEL] May you writhe
in pain and agony
until death seems like
a blessing from above!
[DAN] There's nothing
that can stop me!
I'll fight until the day
I win your heart!
C'mon, you've gotta
pull yourself together!
Wow.
I had no idea that you
cared so much about me.
How could you?]
[ANGEL] That man lacks
beauty and intelligence.
He's pathetic.
He simply deserves to die.
You were beggin' me
to kill you a minute ago.
Quit acting like you're
all high and mighty.
You're no better than him.
You don't have
the right to choose
whether someone lives or dies!
Of course I do.
I'm an angel.
[GRAY] What?
[ANGEL] No...
I'm sorry, what I
meant to say is I'm a
maiden who longs to be an angel.
I have no doubt I'll
become one someday
but I want it so desperately
I can get impatient.
[GRAY] Huh?
[ANGEL] Yes.
I know that one day
my wish will come true.
[ANGEL] And when it does,
the power of my miraculous
Angel magic will
bathe me in its divine
light and wash
away all of my sin.
[GRAY] What sin?
[ANGEL] The worst of all.
Being born human.
You don't seriously
believe that, do you?
I chip away at
my own life whenever
I summon angels,
but I don't mind.
It's a sacrifice I'm willing to
make to become one myself.
[GRAY] Those coins
represent your life force?
And you're throwin' them away?
[ANGEL] What can I say?
I'm ready to trade in these
fake wings for real ones.
The more angelic
power I wield, the more
ugliness I see
in the human world.
[ANGEL] Yes.
This wretched place is
nothing more than a
disgusting cesspit
overflowing with human greed!
To vanish into
the sky like an angel.
That is my wish.
I want to bid farewell to this
rotten world and never return.
[ANGEL]
I will vanish beautifully.
[GRAY] You may be alive,
but you're dead on the inside.
How so?
[GRAY] You can't be happy.
All you ever do is babble
on about "sin" and how
this world is a "rotten" place.
But, you made that choice!
Just look at this guy.
He may be lovesick and insane
but he's honest with himself.
He chooses to live
life to the fullest!
[GRAY] If there's one
thing Fairy Tail's taught me,
it's that no matter how hard
things get you never give up.
We all laugh, yell, and even
cry as hard as we can!
We make the
most out of every,
single day 'cause each
one of 'em counts!
Goodness, you don't
have to yell at me like that.
[GRAY] People like
you make me sick!
The only reason
you wanna die so bad
is because you've
hardly even lived!
[GRAY] If you refuse
to be a part of this world
then you have no right
to call it a "rotten place."
'Cause the truth is, you
don't know anything about it!
[GRAY] The way you spout
off that nonsense, you sound
like a spoiled brat who's
pretending to be an angel!
[ANGEL] You think
it's "nonsense," do you?
[GRAY]
Why even bother vanishing?
There's no need.
'Cause you're pretty
much gone already.
How dare you mock me?
Belittle my deepest wish?
[GRAY] Whoa, what
the hell's happenin' to you?
[ANGEL] Raguel!
Destroy him at once!
[ANGEL] Yes,
that's a wonderful start!
Now, keep at it until
the fool's torn to pieces!
[GRAY] What is that?
It's disgusting.
[Angel chuckles]
[GRAY] This isn't funny!
Can't you see that your own
magic's about to devour you?
[ANGEL] Stay away!
[ANGEL] Prepare to meet your
destruction, you filthy human!
Let me go!
That ain't gonna happen!
Would ya take a look around?
Your beloved angel is about
to take over and kill you!
[ANGEL] But why?
[GRAY] Hasn't anyone
ever told you that the
stronger a spell is,
the more demanding it is?
When a weak-minded wizard
casts a powerful spell,
it can backfire and
engulf its caster!
[ANGEL] I'm not weak-minded!
I'm stronger than
you could ever imagine!
I'm not gonna
argue with you!
Just look at your "angel."
Now tell me,
is this really what
you've been longing
for all of this time?
I guarantee, if this thing takes
you anywhere it's not gonna be
pretty blue skies, but more
like a pit of utter darkness!
[ANGEL] It's so ugly.
[GRAY] Yes, it is!
This is the true form
of the magic you gained!
It's just a parasite, feeding
off your life so it can grow!
This is what
you've become!
If you don't stop it,
there's no goin' back!
[ANGEL] So this is me?
[GRAY] C'mon, you've
gotta snap out of it!
You're not an angel!
You're human!
You're a living, breathing
human but not for long!
I know that's not true.
I'm not human.
I'm an angel!
Wake up, you idiot!
You're gonna vanish
for good when this
lump of flesh
swallows you whole!
[GRAY] This isn't what
you wished for, is it?
[ANGEL] This monster is me?
[GRAY] You've gotta
get it together!
You can't let your magic
get the best of you!
You have to live!
[ANGEL] No, please.
Help me!
[ANGEL] I'm scared.
Make it stop.
[ANGEL] I don't want to vanish.
I want to live.
I want to live!
[GRAY] Get outta here,
ya phony angel!
[GRAY] I'm sendin' you
back where you belong!
[massive explosion]
[GRAY] It's over.
[DAN] Ya gotta admit,
my timing was perfect.
[DAN] At the exact same moment
you destroyed that monster.
I shrunk the core of
Angie's magic to make it
as small as I could
possibly get it.
[DAN] Basically,
you got all your coins back.
[GRAY] And those years
have been added to your life.
I don't understand.
Why did you go to such lengths
to save the life of your enemy?
[GRAY] Huh.
Y'know, that's a
really good question.
I would've felt
like a total jerk
if I had just let you
vanish without a fight.
[ANGEL] Very well, then.
I admit defeat.
[GRAY] There ya go,
spoken like a true angel.
[DAN] Don't you get any ideas
buddy, this cutie's all mine!
[LUCY] One of the seals
has disappeared.
Now there are
only three remaining.
[NATSU] Hey, Lucy!
Listen up!
I know that you can
hear me right now!
Just hang on!
I promise I will save you!
♪
[NATSU] There are
only three of those jerks
left so let's take
'em all out at once!
[HAPPY] That's a good
one comin' from the
very first wizard
to be defeated.
[NATSU] Geez, why didya have
to bring that up again?
[HAPPY] And let's not
forget that you've
been totally helpless
against Michelle!
[NATSU] That's only because
I don't wanna hit a girl!
[HAPPY] Yeah right, that's the
lamest excuse I've ever heard!
[NATSU]
Sorry for bein' a gentleman!
[HAPPY AND NATSU] Next time:
I Hear the Voice of My Friend!
I don't know if you noticed
this, but it feels like
Michelle might be hesitating
when she attacks.
[HAPPY] Oh, so now you're
gentleman and a psychologist?
[NATSU] Shut up!