[NARRATOR]
The Village of the Sun
has been entombed in solid ice.
The members of Fairy Tail
came to the village
at the request of the
Wizard Saint Warrod Sequen.
But, it wasn't long before
treasure hunters from
the Sylph Labyrinth guild,
and members of the dark guild
Succubus Eye attacked them.
The mayhem continued
when the mysterious Doriate
transformed Gray
and Erza into children
using his Art of Regression.
Do they have any chance
of fighting back?
Only time will tell.
[NATSU grunts]
Why can't this stupid
voice just meet me halfway?
[NATSU yelling]
[LUCY] You'd need to train
another hundred years
to stand a chance against us!
Grant the stalwart might
to cleave the heavens--Arms!
You know that tying up my hair
doesn't make it less powerful.
Wait, for real? I was
positive that would work!
[HIROSHI whimpering]
I can't lose, I'm a--
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
[RALA yelling]
Hair Shower Thousand Birds!
[HIROSHI grunting]
[DRAKE yelling]
Now! Lucy Kick!
I'd like to offer
a Virgo kick as well.
[DRAKE groaning]
[LUCY, VIRGO yelling]
[GROUP]
Sayonara!
[VIRGO]
--[WENDY chuckles]
--Solved that problem!
[ERZA yelping]
You used to be so strong.
The Great Titania, now a mere
child at my non-existent mercy.
[ERZA groaning]
Like a helpless lamb. The only
trait you lack is innocence.
[ERZA panting]
--[ERZA screams]
--[MINERVA laughs]
That was great!
Now, let's put an end to it
before it starts to drag.
[chuckles]
[ERZA grunting]
[gasps]
[grunts]
The look on your face.
Simply exquisite.
I'm a kid, but how?
[DORIATE growls]
[GRAY screaming]
[DORIATE]
Uh?
[GRAY cries]
Relivin' old memories?
You aren't the first person
to have some flashbacks
after regression,
but you might just
be the loudest.
You're one messed up kid.
But it'll all be
over, real soon!
No.
It's him. Deliora. Help me!
[GRAY grunting]
[DORIATE] I'm the last guy
you should ask for help.
But I will tell ya
somethin' before you die.
There's one place
here in this world
that people should
avoid at all costs.
[GRAY grunting]
And that place is the
gate to the netherworld.
You and your friends
came right to it.
We're nearly on
top of the thing.
[laughing]
Least you won't have far
to go once you're dead!
[laughing]
[GRAY grunting]
[ULTEAR]
Gray.
[grunts]
[ULTEAR]
Deliora's long gone.
[GRAY] I know, but...
He killed my mom and dad!
And then he killed your mom.
I was so weak. I couldn't--!
[ULTEAR]
You were never weak.
But for the sake
of your friends,
you have to be brave now.
Forget the past.
Defeat the threat before you.
[GRAY grunts]
[GRAY]
My friends?
Defeat the threat before me.
[ULTEAR]
Yes. You can do this.
I'll be watching.
[GRAY]
Okay.
[GRAY yells]
[DORIATE yelps]
An ice wizard?
[grunts]
[GRAY]
Cages of ice...
A demon.
Childhood.
Moon Drip.
[GRAY] Everything I wanna
forget, I've found here.
[GRAY exhales]
That was pathetic.
You made me lose my
head with one spell.
Won't happen again.
This curse of ice.
Was that you as well?
[DORIATE laughs]
Mighta been. So what if it was?
Well, then first
of all, I'd tell you
that your ice smells
as terrible as it looks.
And right after that, I'd give
you a taste of the real deal.
Oh, yeah?
[laughing]
[LUCY, WENDY panting]
[FLARE] The Eternal Flame
isn't far from here!
Might be a good place to
try and find the others!
If we can't find
'em near there,
then where else
could they have gone?
Everyone hang in there.
We'll turn you back to normal,
there's gotta be a way.
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
So, could I take a nap
while we're waitin,' or--?
If I have to watch this thing
fly in circles, then so do you.
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
This beast, could it
have something to do
with the village?
It seems doubtful.
[GRAY]
Then first of all, I'd tell you
that your ice smells
as terrible as it looks.
And right after I that, I'd give
you a taste of the real deal.
Oh, would ya?
Let's see you try it.
Then maybe you'll realize
just how screwed you are.
The Art of Regression might
make you look like a child,
but that's just
icing on the cake.
Strength, speed, endurance,
and magic also take a hit.
Is it starting to sink in yet?
You're helpless as a rabbit
cornered by a wolf,
and this wolf will
savor the meal.
Where should I start?
[ice cracking]
[DORIATE]
How'd this get here?
[GRAY] I decided to
add to the landscape.
You might be the wolf
in this scenario.
But this rabbit's still got
some tricks up his sleeve.
--[ice cracking]
--[DORIATE yelps]
[DORIATE yelling]
[DORIATE grunts]
How did you pull that off?
[GRAY]
When you backed away from me,
I snuck it under your feet.
Simple. You may
have all the brawn,
but I've got more brain
than you ever will.
[DORIATE growls]
And that's all I really
need to beat you.
My ideas are my
sharpest weapons.
That's Maker Magic 101,
and you're about
to get a crash course.
Sorry, I'm not impressed.
[DORIATE grunting]
Making your thoughts
reality takes magic power,
and I doubt you have enough
to make a toothpick.
[DORIATE grunts]
Hiding won't help you!
[GRAY]
I'm right where you left me.
Uh?
It's not my fault
that you fell for the
same trick twice in a row.
[DORIATE gasps]
[DORIATE yelps]
[grunts]
[yelps]
[DORIATE screaming]
You're dead!
[DORIATE grunts]
Now, Ice Make Hammer! Uh!
Aw, man!
Are ya out of ideas already?
Give me some credit.
I didn't get this far
without improvising.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Keep throwing your little
parlor tricks at me.
In the end, it won't do
anything to save you--Uh.
Snow Cone!
[DORIATE grunts]
[laughing]
[GRAY]
What's the matter, gettin' cold?
It's hard to believe
you froze this village
when a little snow can
give you the chills.
[growls]
You're no ice wizard.
Whoever turned this place
into a tundra, it wasn't you.
[GRAY] You don't have
the power to pull that off.
[DORIATE growls]
Truth is, you have to weaken
people to even stand a chance.
You're just a small
fry with a big ego.
If I wanted to, I could
end your life in a flash.
But I think I'd like to hear
something from you first.
Something far worse than death
to a proud and mighty warrior.
I wanna hear you
beg me for mercy.
Plead for forgiveness.
Do that, and I might let you
leave of your own volition.
[grunts]
You can't abandon your pride
for vengeance, Minerva.
[gasps]
Dedicate your magic to
helping out your friends.
To protecting everyone you love.
[MINERVA grunts]
[ERZA]
It's not too late.
You can still turn your
back on the darkness.
So, you'd rather lecture me
than save your own skin?
That's fine!
But, this is the last time
you'll insult me
with your arrogance!
[MINERVA yells]
[ERZA grunts]
My body's back! Let's see
if my strength is too!
[MINERVA yelps]
[ERZA yells]
[MINERVA grunts]
[MINERVA groaning]
Has Doriate been defeated?
Well, it's no matter.
It will be just as fun
to kill you at your best.
[MINERVA] And if she uses
her Nakagami Armor...
[MINERVA]
...I'll have a surprise waiting.
She won't know what hit her.
Before we start, you might
want to cover up down there.
[ERZA gasps]
[chuckles]
That makes two of us.
[MINERVA grunts]
[yelps]
When did this happen?
[chuckles]
Have you no shame?
Sorry, I was running
on pure instinct.
Your skirt was the first
thing I got a hold of.
[NATSU]
Whoa!
--[thud]
--[NATSU grunts]
Man, I'm big again!
I was just starting to get
the hang of being a kid.
[grunting]
What the heck's going
on around here?
Okay, I wasn't expecting this.
[DORIATE growling]
[growling continues]
[DORIATE roaring]
[GRAY yelps]
[roaring]
What's the matter, big guy?
Did you break the
spell out of rage,
or are you just too stupid
to control it?
[roaring]
[GRAY grunts]
[DORIATE roaring]
[GRAY grunting]
[GRAY gasps]
[DORIATE groaning]
Oh, man.
Was this guy keeping
Satan Soul magic in reserve?
[heartbeat]
[GRAY]
Wait... I know this feeling.
Can't be. There's no way!
[DORIATE growls]
I thought he
was human, but...
[DORIATE growls]
I was dead wrong.
He's... from the Book of
Zeref! No doubt about it.
[DORIATE roaring]
[GRAY grunts]
His power's through the roof!
I need to think
of something, quick!
[gasps]
[roaring]
[GRAY grunts]
You gotta be
freakin' kidding me!
[NATSU grunts]
This is getting old.
[ERZA grunting]
[MINERVA]
So.
[ERZA gasps]
[MINERVA]
Doriate's still kicking.
Once again, I have
the advantage.
Hey. Look down.
[MINERVA]
Uh?
No! Why was I affected?
[grunts]
Has he lost control?
'Kay. Something's missing here.
I can see my feet again!
Somethin' musta
turned us into kids!
Little blondie.
You're so cute!
I know, right?
Can we skip the vanity
and do somethin' 'bout this?
Not cool.
Totally lame.
Ya dig?
[grunts]
[CARLA, HAPPY screaming]
[CARLA, HAPPY grunt]
--[GRAY] Hey. What's the matter?
--[CARLA, HAPPY groaning]
I don't know what happened,
but my wings suddenly
stopped wantin' to wing.
You've turned into
a kitten, Happy!
Gray? Why do you look
like a pre-pubescent?
Don't look now, but the
culprit's right behind you.
[CARLA, HAPPY]
Uh?
[roaring]
[BOTH] That's not a
culprit, it's a monster!
[HAPPY]
Where did he come from?
[growling]
I gotta end this before
he does some major damage!
[DORIATE growling]
No! My power's gone!
Okay. I'll just have to
freeze him in his tracks.
Crap! That didn't help.
[DORIATE growling]
[GRAY grunts]
Oh, no! Gray!
[groans]
That nearly did me in...
and it was only one hit!
The Art of Regression might
make you look like a child,
but that's just
icing on the cake.
Strength, speed, endurance,
and magic also take a hit.
Is it starting to sink in yet?
And that's not the worst of it.
His power is way
stronger than before.
I'm in trouble.
Another hit, and
I might be a goner!
[DORIATE growls]
[GRAY]
I can't even move!
[DORIATE growling]
[GRAY] There's gotta
be a way out of this.
Come on, I'm surrounded by ice.
I should have
the advantage here!
[GRAY]
Wait a minute.
[DORIATE yelping]
Are you out of ideas already?
[DORAITE growling]
[GRAY]
Could that be it?
Is it really that simple?
[BOTH]
Hold on!
[GRAY grunts]
Did ya have to wait
till the very last second?
We're having a hard
time with these wings,
so this is as fast as we can go!
[GRAY grunts]
[GRAY]
Yes! I was right after all!
[GRAY] I was so busy wasting
my magic I didn't realize
the frozen grass had
actually done some damage.
Normally, his weight
would have been enough
to shatter it into
a million pieces.
But whatever magic
this smelly ice is made of
was strong enough to hurt him.
[GRAY]
I wish I knew more about it,
but for now, I won't look
a gift horse in the mouth.
[GRAY] I just need to hit him
with this ice's magic power.
But how?
[DORIATE roaring]
[GRAY, CARLA, HAPPY screaming]
[GRAY]
How am I gonna do that?
If the ice wasn't so resistant,
I could control it
and be done with 'im.
[GRAY]
I don't need to control it!
[GRAY grunting]
[GRAY] If I channel its
magic power through me,
I can skip melting
it altogether!
[GRAY] I was so freaked
out by its creepy magic
and all the bad memories,
I couldn't think straight.
I never gave myself
a chance to try!
Don't just stand there,
ugly! Let's do this!
[DORIATE roaring]
I'm lending you my body for
a spell! Don't let me down!
[GRAY yelling]
[DORIATE groaning]
[GRAY groaning]
[DORIATE yelling]
[BOTH]
Yay! Yay! Yay!
[BOTH gasping]
[BOTH laughing]
[GRAY grunts]
Way to put that creep on ice!
[GRAY]
Thanks.
That was an amazing spell!
It's 'cause of this ice.
It's packing crazy power.
It had a weird feel to it,
but it was also, sort of...
[GRAY] Anyway, I think
it's time I got some answers.
[footsteps]
[DORIATE groans]
[DORIATE chuckles]
The netherworld gate
just busted wide open.
All thanks to you.
[GRAY grunts]
You'll realize the
consequences soon enough.
There's no turning back.
[trees cracking]
[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
[GRAY grunts]
[CARLA, HAPPY] Oh, come on!
Can't we catch a break?
Maybe I should've taken
old tusk face down.
All this changing back and forth
crap is getting really annoying.
[LUCY]
Natsu.
What a relief!
I thought we'd lost you!
We wouldn't have if he'd just
stayed with the rest of us.
Long time no see.
[NATSU gasps]
It's you!
[FLARE squeaks]
Cool it! She's not the enemy.
Flare is from this village
and she wants to help us out.
[NATSU] So, what you're
telling me is she's a giant?
[FLARE groans]
[WENDY] No, silly.
The giants just raised her.
[NATSU]
Hmmm.
Uh. Stop staring.
I'm sorry about
your home, and friends.
This must be hard for you.
[FLARE]
Uh.
I swear on our guild's name.
We'll bring back this village
and everybody in it.
[gasps]
We think the Eternal Flame
might be able to turn
everything back to normal.
Flare was just showing us
the way when we ran into you.
[NATSU]
I see.
I'm still chasing that
voice from before.
I thought I heard it
coming from this mountain.
This isn't a mountain.
Uh?
It's the village's deity.
Our great protector.
[NATSU]
Uhh?
[LUCY, WENDY gasp]
[FLARE]
This is the Eternal Flame.
[NATSU]
What?!
[LUCY, WENDY gasp]
There's no way that's a flame!
Sir Warrod did mention
the flame was frozen.
But he didn't say it was huge!
If I didn't see it,
I wouldn't believe it.
If this bad boy has the power
to restore the village,
we should focus all
our efforts on thawing it out.
Now we just have to
figure out how to do that.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
I think something's coming.
[NATSU]
Gray?
[LUCY]
Happy?
[WENDY]
Carla?
Run for it!
It's got an appetite!
[ALL grunt]
--[WINGED MONSTER squawking]
--[GRAY, CARLA, HAPPY panting]
[screaming]
What is that?!
Uh. I don't know,
but it's hungry
and we're the next
dish on the menu!
Someone throw a spell already!
Turn around and ice it, Gray!
[GRAY] I can't afford to
waste magic power right now!
[NATSU]
Why?
Because I think I found
a way to unfreeze the village
and get things back to normal!
[NATSU grunts]
Really?
Raven Tail?
What is she doing here?
Don't worry about her!
You really think
you can melt this ice?
I'm not a hundred
percent certain.
But I'm sure as
hell gonna try to!
All right then!
I can deal with this ugly bird
while you melt that mountain!
Do that and we might
have a chance!
[GRAY]
What?
[NATSU] That's the Eternal
Flame! Can you do it?
Watch me.
[BOTH]
I'm counting on ya! Go!
[LUCY] Fire and ice.
The two magic types roar.
Natsu brings his flames to bear
on that one-eyed bird monster,
while Gray tries to thaw
the Eternal Flame.
Do they have what it takes,
or have we already lost?
Natsu and Gray.
A joint struggle of souls.
Will they save
the Village of the Sun
and the giants trapped within?
What shocking truths will,
at last, be revealed?
Next time: "Voice of the Flame"!
Natsu's fire gives
birth to a miracle.