[WARROD]
E.N.D.? Tell me more.
[NATSU]
He's from the Book of Zeref.
Apparently my old man, Igneel,
tried to take him
down way back when.
Zeref, you say?
I haven't heard that
name in a tree's age.
I've been trying to find Igneel
ever since he disappeared.
I thought if I found
out more about E.N.D.,
it might lead me to him.
Atlas Flame told us
there was history
between Igneel and the demon.
[WARROD] Hmm. Sorry,
but I don't know anything.
However, there might
be a connection
between this E.N.D.
character and Tartaros.
They're an eerie group of
wizards, shrouded in secrecy.
No one knows how many
members they have,
or where their guild is located.
But I've heard
stories from people
claiming to have stumbled
on their gatherings.
And all of them came to the
exact same conclusion.
The Tartaros rituals are
for worshipping demons.
[GRAY grunts]
Now we don't know for certain,
but the Four Emperors of
Ishgar have a grim suspicion.
We believe Tartaros may
be in the possession
of a demon from
the Book of Zeref.
You're kidding! A guild
with a demon? Creepy!
If that's true, it could be
the one we're lookin' for!
[GRAY]
So tusk face was involved.
I knew I was onto somethin'.
[NATSU growls]
[SILVER] Home sweet home.
As grey and lifeless as always.
No matter how many
times I see it,
it always makes me shiver.
I'm sure you've heard.
Fairy Tail won the
Grand Magic Games.
Tenacious fools.
This proves their Tenrou Team
had way too much
power to begin with!
[LOEWEN] They certainly know
how to attract attention.
[BABARAKI]
Too much attention.
Their victory made them
more admired than ever.
I think we should consider
banning the tournament!
[NOCRA] It's the most popular
magic related event
in the Fiore Kingdom, and you
think we should take it away?
[tap, tap]
Enough. Back to business.
We're here to discuss Tartaros,
and the growing
threat they represent.
[ORG]
Mm.
[GRAN DOMA]
As I'm sure you're aware,
seven dark guilds we thought
were affiliated with Tartaros
have been wiped out over
the past several days.
We don't know why or
who's responsible.
But it's certainly an
unwelcome favor.
If a legitimate guild
is behind this,
Tartaros may already be
planning to strike back.
[LOEWEN] Could it be,
oh, what's their name?
That small band of
dark guild hunters.
Do you mean Crime Sorcière?
Perhaps, but this move
seems too bold.
I wouldn't put it past those
contemptible Fairies
to pull off something like this.
They have always favored
flexing their muscles
over using their brains.
[ORG]
Should we just adopt the policy
of blaming Fairy Tail
every time there's a crisis?
That sounds lazy to me.
[LEIJI]
Are you saying that they're
above suspicion, Master Org?
Not quite. I merely suggest
that we keep an open mind.
What if Tataros
itself is to blame?
They could be taking
over their branch guilds
for a purpose we
have yet to consider.
And that would be?
Not sure, but there are
many plausible reasons.
They could be reinforcing
their own numbers,
or purging all of their
low-level personnel.
[MAGIC COUNCIL MEMBERS laugh]
[SID] So they're
cannibalizing their allies?
[LEIJI] Quite the
brilliant strategy.
[LOEWEN] Tartaros is
more than ready for war.
They have no need
for additional forces.
[BABARAKI] Has old age finally
caught up with your mind?
Not so fast. I think Master
Org's theory has merit.
[SID]
Chairman!
[GRAN DOMA]
Whatever the truth,
we've put off this
problem far too long.
It's time we dealt with it.
We don't know as
much as I would like,
but if we can crush Tartaros,
the Baram Alliance will
certainly disappear.
I propose that we employ the
full power of the Council
to remove this blight
from the face of Fiore.
[SID, NOCRA]
Uh...
[LEIJI]
Mm...
[ORG]
Hm.
It's about time they had a
fire lit under their asses.
We might be one Etherion blast
away from a lasting peace.
At this rate,
the Baram Alliance and their
guilds will be gone for good.
--[door opens]
--Uh?!
There's an emergency situation!
[LEIJI]
Hm?
What's the fuss about?
You Fool! This better
be important!
[MESSENGER 234A] I'm terribly
sorry, but there's an intruder!
[ORG grunts]
[CROWD murmurs]
[MAGIC COUNCIL MEMBERS scream]
[DORANBOLT groans]
My head. Hey,
what just happened?
[groans] Get up.
This is serious!
Come on, I'm not
doin' this solo.
Wake up! Lahar!
My god. He's dead.
[groans]
[whimpers] No way.
Hello? Is anyone alive?
[DORANBOLT yelps, groans]
Damnit.
[ORG]
Doranbolt.
Uh... Uh! Master Org!
We're not out of danger!
[ORG groans]
[DORANBOLT gasps]
You can't be alive.
Killing all of you
was the whole point.
Your pals played along, but I
guess you need some convincing.
Explosion.
Damn you!
[ORG]
Doranbolt. Run away!
[DORANBOLT grunts]
I can't do that!
There's no reason for you
to die with the rest of us.
Hate to burst your bubble,
but there's no running
from my explosions.
[ORG]
Leave! Do it now!
[DORANBOLT groans]
The name's Jackal, by the way.
One of the Nine Demon
Gates of Tartaros.
Tell that to your
friends in hell.
They should know the name of
the man who slaughtered them.
Tell them I enjoyed it.
[ORG groans] Live! Find
what justice means to you,
and defend it to the end.
That's an order!
[JACKAL chuckles]
[DORANBOLT]
Master Org!
[CROWD screams]
[FAIRY TAIL MEMBERS]
Cheers!
Hey, Mira, could you bring
me a pint of the good stuff?
Better make that a double.
Coming right up!
[ROMEO]
It's the middle of the day, Dad!
[ELFMAN]
Wanna tell me why you're
eyein' my sister
like that, Warren?
Elfman, you gotta calm down!
[MAKAROV] Hmm. Minerva's fallen
pretty far, hasn't she?
Yes.
[MAKAROV]
What about her father?
He was Sabertooth's
former master, as I recall.
He hasn't been seen or
heard from since the tournament.
[LAKI]
No loss there.
Sting is a much better master
than that old crank ever was.
It must be awesome to have
such a hot, young hunk
for a guildmaster!
Ain't that the truth, sister.
I should probably make sure
the Council knows Sabertooth
is under new management.
[ERZA] I plan to contact Sting,
as well, once things slow down.
I have a surprise for
you, my darling Gray!
[GRAY]
Uh...
Something warm for
you to munch on!
Ah!
[JUVIA]
I call them Graybuns!
Well, they do look pretty tasty,
but it would feel weird
to gnaw on my own face.
I thought you'd say that.
Guess I'll keep all the
Graybuns for myself.
Which means you get to
enjoy these hot Juvibuns!
[GRAY]
You set me up!
Did I miss something?
I could have sworn he already
gave Juvia a clear-cut answer
in the form of a 'No'.
I don't think she accepted it.
[chomp] Pretty good!
[JUVIA screams]
Oh yeah! It tastes super manly!
You have an amazing talent
for saying the wrong thing.
This is awful!
Not only did another man
get a mouthful of my buns,
he said they tasted
like masculinity!
You went through
all the trouble.
I might as well eat one.
Oh, my darling! That's a--
Graybun.
[GRAY grunts]
I found something.
[ALL]
Hm?
It's about E.N.D. Apparently,
he's a super demon.
Compared to Lullaby and Deliora,
he's on a different
level altogether.
It really is the most powerful
Demon from the Book of Zeref.
So, how do we beat it?
No clue. I'm not even sure what
the Book of Zeref really is.
Don't look at me.
Zeref created demons.
They're pure evil.
After he was done,
he committed the spells for
summoning them into those books.
[HAPPY] So if someone
got their hands on one,
they could summon a demon
just by reading them?
[CARLA] Yes, and each demon
has a book dedicated to it.
So, there's a chance
Tartaros has one of 'em.
I'd bet it's Probably the one
for summoning E.N.D.
Also, there's the fact Igneel
tried to take the
creep out before.
Yeah. I figured it out.
Huh? Figured what out?
We gotta take the
fight to Tartaros!
Count me in!
[LUCY]
You're both brain dead!
Besides, there is way too
much we don't know about
their guild yet. We don't
even know where they are.
Let alone how many creep-tastic
demons they'll
be throwing our way. Just how
do you plan to take it to them?
I don't know. Still, it might
get us closer to finding Igneel.
[WENDY]
That's true, and Grandeeney.
Who knows, maybe Metalicana has
somethin' to do with this, too.
[door opens]
Listen up, everybody!
I've got horrible news!
[NATSU]
Uh.
--[ERZA] Uh...
--[MAKAROV] Mm?
[JUVIA, GRAY]
Uh?
--[WENDY] Uh!
--[GAJEEL] Hm.
[LUCY gasps]
And here I was startin' to get
lonely. What a sweetheart.
I assume you heard what
happened upstairs.
Don't be stupid.
You know I can't use
magic inside this cell.
That said, it was hard not
to notice the explosions.
You're telling me everything
you know about Tartaros.
Is that so?
I don't talk for free.
But you'll get what you want,
if you release the seis.
[DORANBOLT] I don't have
that kind of authority.
Then I suggest that you go
and talk to someone who does.
[DORANBOLT growls]
[DORANBOLT] The Council
members. They're all dead.
[COBRA]
Uh!
Hm. Sounds like they got
you pretty good.
I lost a friend today.
I'm not in the mood for
games, understand?
I'll give you just one more
chance. Talk or die here.
[COBRA] Hmph. Not until you
release the Oracion Seis.
You're not the only
one with friends.
[DORANBOLT growls]
[COBRA] Tell you what. I'll give
you a little tip, on the house.
[KYOKA gasps]
It's been a while, Silver.
Looking good, Kyoka.
I'm digging the evil entourage.
[KYOKA] I'm surprised
you came in human form.
[SILVER]
Manly, isn't it? Suits me.
[KYOKA] Any sign of
Jackal or Tempester yet?
[FRANMALTH]
They're too busy
stirrin' up trouble for the
council. He, he, he, he.
So, the operation has already
begun in earnest, has it?
Very well, let's show the humans
the power of the netherworld,
and the hell the Nine Demon
Gates can unleash.
[COBRA] No one in Tartaros
is remotely human.
They're all demons.
From the Book of Zeref.
[DORANBOLT gulps]
[COBRA]
Their master's name is E.N.D.
The most powerful demon
there's ever been.
[laughs] Sounds like
Jackal went all out!
The poor fools didn't even know
what hit them! Ha, ha, ha!
How much are the council
members lives worth?
Ohh, I'm droolin' at
the thought of it!
[TORAFUZAR]
Enough, Franmalth.
Quit laughing like
a damn banshee.
It makes us look like
undignified animals.
[EZEL] Demons got no
business being dignified!
Let me take the next
shot at them, Kyoka!
I got a fever, and the only
cure is making corpses!
Don't forget, all stories have
an order to them, Ezel.
This one has just begun.
In fact, one could say
this is merely the prologue.
Precisely. Just calm down, Ezel.
You'll have a task all to
yourself soon enough.
Fine. But don't make
me wait much longer!
Jackal and Tempester
shouldn't get all the fun!
[TORAFUZAR]
Mm.
[KEYES] Netherworld,
we beseech thee.
Grant us your dark blessings
that we may serve you.
[KYOKA] And may our lord,
Zeref, be pleased.
[SILVER]
Hm.
[KYOKA] All that we do,
we do for him. Our creator.
Now, then, let's pay
humanity a visit.
[CROWD chatting]
[YAJIMA sighs]
It's such a terrible tragedy.
So hard to believe it's true.
I heard all nine of the council
members were killed instantly.
[YAJIMA]
That's not the half of it.
There were one hundred
nineteen other casualties.
A truly dark day.
[BIXLOW]
Guess it's a good thing
you quit the Council
when you did.
Shame on you! Have some
respect for the dead!
We do. We're just glad you
weren't there with them.
Oh, well. I guess
I should've known.
Something was bound to
happen in Era eventually.
You think? But why?
[YAJIMA]
Because of what it represents.
Era serves as headquarters
for the Magic Council.
Making it a symbol that holds
all the legitimate guilds, and,
by extension, the
wizards, together.
Being a council member means
you share part of that symbol,
and the responsibilities
that come with it.
I did everything I could
to serve the people.
But as you are aware, the
council was far from perfect.
It's no secret that
it was plagued
with administration problems.
Jellal being one of
the most prevalent.
Between their occasional
lapses in judgment,
and the sheer number
of overbearing policies,
I never found a chance
to really make my mark.
When I finally quit the Council
and opened up my restaurant,
I was actually relieved.
It felt like a great weight had
been lifted from my shoulders.
[FRIED]
As it should.
[YAJIMA] Indeed, a weight
had been lifted, but...
You still had some
doubts, right?
I couldn't shake the feeling
that we were heading
towards calamity.
Authority will always give
rise to strong opposition,
it's the way of the world.
And Considering the Council's
utterly uncompromising nature,
it was only a matter of
time before a bad decision
ticked off the wrong
kind of people.
But this mess...
I never could have predicted.
[BIXLOW]
Mm..
[EVERGREEN]
Okay, that's it.
I know the place is empty,
but that doesn't mean
you don't have to work!
Yeah, well. That uniform
doesn't work for you.
No.
You're the reason
I'm wearing it!
Jerks. Sheesh.
Ever since we won the games,
you've done nothing but complain
about all the heavy-duty
jobs we've had.
That's why we're
working in this dump.
You know, you could
at least pretend
to care that I'm
right in front of you.
[FRIED] Preparing food
happens to be my specialty.
[BIXLOW] And serving food
is my specialty, baby!
[TOMMEN]
Serve it up!
[EVERGREEN] Well, I suppose,
being sexy is my specialty.
Anyway. Why isn't Loxus
back with the supplies yet?
It's been hours.
Five Jewel says
he lost his way.
He's able to defeat an army,
but falls to menial tasks.
--[door creaks]
--[gasps]
Speak of the devil!
Uh!
Whoosh.
[YAJIMA screams]
[BIXLOW screams]
[EVERGREEN screams]
Whirr.
[YAJIMA gasps]
What is this guy?
Yajima, no!
[FRIED groans]
Ka-boom!
[screams]
Fwoosh.
[YAJIMA screams]
Mr. Yajima!
Fairy Machine Gun! Leprechaun!
You're helpless.
[CROWD shouting]
[EVERGREEN groaning]
Ever!
He creamed us.
[YAJIMA stammers]
Who the hell are you?
[STRANGER]
I have no name.
Though humans have
a word for me.
They call me disaster.
A force of nature.
[BIXLOW groaning] What's with
his magic? I can't move!
And he's barely even touched us.
[STRANGER]
The netherworld gate has opened.
--Humanity will be judged.
--[YAJIMA groaning]
Netherworld gate?
He's from Tartaros,
no doubt about it.
[FRIED] So, that means...
It wasn't just the nine.
They're going after former
members of the Council as well.
But why? What could
Tartaros be after?
Say your prayers.
Let him go!
[STRANGER]
Too late.
[YAJIMA screams]
Yajima!
[STRANGER growls]
[YAJIMA]
Uh.
[FRIED]
Uh!
[BIXLOW]
Hm.
[STRANGER]
Mm.
[LAXUS] Those are my
pals you're messin' with.
If you thought you're
getting away with this,
you're in for a real shock.
[LUCY] Someone from Tartaros
calling himself "Disaster"
attacked our friend Yajima, a
former member of the Council.
He over-powered the
Thunder Legion,
but now he has to deal
with a ticked off Laxus.
It doesn't matter who
we're up against,
Fairy Tail will fight anyone
that hurts our members.
Even if they're demons!
As the rubble starts to fall,
our fury begins to rise!
Next time!
Tartaros Chapter, Prologue
- Fairies vs. Netherworld!
Then again, Laxus has
enough fury for all of us.