As I've said, I dislike humans,
but they can be so entertaining.
You, defeating the
Underworld King?
Ridiculous.
Just watch us!
[NARRATOR]
The Twin Dragons of Sabertooth
came to the aid of
their fallen guildmate
and took on Mard Geer himself.
This gave Minerva, Erza, and
the Exceeds a chance to escape.
The group searched the ruins of
Plutogrim for the control room,
hoping to stop the detonation
of thousands of Face bombs.
But the fungal Franmalth
proves to be a deceptive guide.
[TORAFUZAR] Only the full
might of the Etherious
can conquer such powerful foes.
[TEMPESTER]
Let's end this.
[NARRATOR] Natsu and Gajeel
kicked into high gear
and switched to their
dual-element modes,
combining lightning and
shadow with fire and iron.
But will this be enough to
conquer the bloodthirsty demons
in their terrifying
Etherious forms?
[NATSU yelling]
[GAJEEL yelling]
Who have they turned into?
Flame Lotus Exploding
Lightning Blade!
Iron Shadow Dragon Roar!
You'll meet your demise in
the depths of the Underworld.
Dark Deluge!
[NARRATOR]
Our heroes put up a good fight,
but Torafuzar unleashed
his "Dark Deluge" curse,
engulfing everything in a wave
of black, poisonous water.
With his comrades rendered
unconscious by the flood,
Gajeel found himself
running out of options,
and running out of air.
But then...
[GAJEEL]
Don't you touch her!
Levy!
Pull yourself together!
Wake up, kid!
You gave me that breath
of air just now, right?
There more where
that came from?
[LEVY]
He wants me to do it again?
[LEVY gasps]
[LEVY] Uh, hang on! I think
he's got the wrong idea!
I knew he was in trouble,
so I shared some of my
own breath with him!
[GAJEEL] Hurry up and give
the others some air, too!
They're gonna drown
if you don't!
[LEVY] But if I do that,
I won't have any left.
I don't wanna drown with them.
I mean, I didn't even
know if it would work,
and the only reason I gave it
to him because he was closest.
Yeah, that's it!
What in the hell
are ya stallin' for?
Use your magic and
make us some air!
[LEVY] Yeah, he's right!
What the heck was I thinking?
I should've written an
air spell to begin with
instead of doing that!
How embarrassing!
Solid Script Air!
[BOTH gasping]
Sorry!
They're still breathing?
[GAJEEL] Now help
Salamander and the others!
[LEVY]
Right!
I owe you kiddo. Big time!
[yelling]
[screaming]
Behold the greatest defense
of the Nine Demon Gates.
I can alter my body's hardness
to deflect whatever
attack comes at me.
Therefore, my skin is
resistant to your pitiful iron.
[GAJEEL]
Damn.That hurt.
The iron on your
skin helped stave off
the poison in the water,
but it's abundantly clear that
you are finally starting to feel
its effects.
You just bought enough time to
see all your comrades perish.
[growls]
Humanity's era is over.
You did put up a valiant effort,
but you were no match
for the Dark Deluge.
The poison will slow down
your body's processes,
and then everyone in your guild
will drown together as one.
[LEVY] We have some air for now,
but the carbon in the water
means it'll be
hard to make more.
If we're trapped here much
longer, we're gonna die.
[TORAFUZAR]
This is the end for you!
[LEVY]
C'mon, Gajeel.
[ORG]
And once again,
we have Gajeel of
Phantom Lord before us.
Honestly now, how many times
has it been just this year?
[GAJEEL chuckles]
[BELNO]
Gajeel, wait!
For another lecture?
Don't ask me why I
waste my breath on you,
but you should strongly consider
leaving Phantom Lord.
I'll leave when
I'm ready to leave.
It's none of your business.
When guilds engage in
such wretched behavior,
it is my business.
It must be stopped.
[GAJEEL]
I think you'd better stop.
You know you're talking
to Black Steel Gajeel,
the Iron Dragon
Slayer, right, hag?
[BELNO]
"Iron-Headed," you mean.
I've seen countless
tough guys like you,
all with a huge chip
on their shoulder.
And all you really want to try
to do is hide your loneliness.
The hell you say?!
[BELNO] I know that being a
"do-gooder" isn't your style.
However,
someone like you could live
a life that has true meaning.
[laughing]
Oh yeah? My life's
got tons of meaning!
Actually, I've got
something big happenin' soon.
We're taking down
those Fairy failures!
[NATSU] Check it out, Lucy, it's
like this job was made for us!
Don't waste my time, Natsu!
I need to pay my
rent this month!
This one's a piece of cake!
Then we'll take another one
and make more money!
"In search of somebody
who can teach me
how to grill tasty,
golden-brown fish."
You've gotta be kidding me.
That sounds like something
that takes a little finesse,
and I'll bet you don't even
know what that word means.
She's got ya there, pal.
And besides,
you want an expert on how to
make the yummiest fishies,
then look no further
than yours truly.
Although I prefer it so
raw, it's still wiggling.
That sounds disgusting.
But maybe you and I should have
a little cook off, ya down?
Aye, sir! Hope you like
the taste of shame!
What? This is an even
bigger waste of time!
[gasps]
Wait a sec!
Do ya have to barbeque
it right here?
[NATSU] Woohoo!
My grill is fired up now!
[HAPPY] Too bad, 'cause you're
messin' with the fishie slayer!
[LUCY] Stop being petty
and find us a real job!
And it better be one
that pays real money!
[LEVY]
Well, what a surprise.
You can smile.
Shut up, ya little busybody.
But you're still a jerk!
[GAJEEL]
They murdered her, too.
The city's fine though, nothing
like what Gray described.
It would seem that this
killer is the stealthy type.
[GAJEEL] I failed. I should've
gotten here sooner.
We did our best.
[GAJEEL] You told me I could
live a life with true meaning.
I wish I could've gotten
the chance to let you know
that I took those
words to heart.
To show you who I've become.
Even though I was
a no good punk,
you were lookin' out for me.
[GAJEEL] I'm so sorry I
couldn't look out for you.
All I can do now is get revenge.
No, I should heed your
advice more than ever.
That's the best way I can
truly honor your life.
I'll never forget what else
you said to me that day.
The truth be told, you remind me
quite a bit of my own late son.
I ain't gonna die here today!
I hope you're watchin'
this somehow, lady!
I ain't some pissed-off piece
of scrap metal anymore!
I went out lookin' for that
meaningful life and I found it!
You see?
Now I live to protect
those that helped me.
The only way I really know how.
They gave my life meaning.
And no one's gonna
take that away!
Impossible!
How could that weak iron break
through my defenses like that?
No. That's not iron.
He must've absorbed
the carbon in the water.
He turned my curse against me.
Gajeel's a lot smarter
than he lets on.
That was brilliant.
He used it to make steel!
[yelling]
[GAJEEL]
Steel Dragon Sword!
[screaming]
[GAJEEL chuckles]
Okay. Well, Salamander,
you owe me a song.
Everyone's still down, and
there's one more demon to go.
Ah, man!
You may've just
defeated a Demon Gate,
but it's cost you
your magic power.
You fought well human. Now die!
I must say I'm surprised.
You should be dead.
Or still in agony.
He left some sort of mist.
[FRIED] Bixlow! Ever!
You have to resist!
[LAXUS]
No one else is gonna die here.
Not while I'm around!
[FRIED]
Laxus, shield your mouth!
What're you doing?!
Nobody has ever taken in
that many Bane Particles
and survived.
Last one up. Déjà vu.
No matter.
Defeating you in
your weakened state
should prove to be an easy task.
Come on.
Whoosh!
It's completely up to me again.
Do something!
[yelling]
I don't understand this.
Did you neutralize the poison?
I'm running solely
on vengeance.
Whoosh!
[gasps]
You hurt my friends.
And nobody has ever
done that and survived!
This is for Fairy Tail!
[TEMPESTER]
He's just as powerful as before,
but more fierce.
Bring it on.
Yes. It'll be my pleasure.
Vwum.
[TEMPESTER]
Ka-bam.
Vwu-wum.
[yelling]
Whoosh!
[TEMPESTER] What is this?
Why won't he attack?
[TEMPESTER]
Could it be?
But how?
No way!
You're not even human are you?
Wait. What's he talkin' about?
You didn't recover.
Your body is teeming
with Bane Particles
and you're still able to stand?
Your organs should
be liquefied by now.
That's why you're
just standing there
and not launching any
attacks, isn't it?
I guess my secret's out huh?
That means I'd better
end this, quickly.
This is the end, you fool.
Kerfwoosh!
Laxus, no!
[LAXUS]
Heh.
Can you even call
this stuff fire?
It's not hot enough to burn.
Is this the best you can do?
[LAXUS yelling]
You're sick.
The poison is coursing
through your veins,
so why do you still fight?
Because nothing's gonna
stop me from getting revenge
for what you did to Fairy Tail!
Holy crap.
[coughs]
[GAJEEL]
You okay?
He must've taken a hit.
Now stay down.
[TEMPESTER]
You're quite remarkable.
[TEMPESTER] A normal human
would be dead by now,
or praying for the end
to take away their pain.
But clearly you're
no normal human.
However, your entire
species is pitifully weak.
I'm a life form far above yours.
Etherious.
You were foolish to believe
you could defeat me.
For I am Tempester the Immortal.
[TEMPESTER yelling]
I missed?
[LAXUS]
Lightning Dragon Jaw!
You may've bested
me once human,
but I swear it will
not happen again.
Ya know, I feel exactly
the same way about it.
[coughing]
[BIXLOW coughing]
[TEMPESTER]
That means I'll see you soon.
In the netherworld.
[LAXUS] This is the second
time you've brought harm
to my family.
[LAXUS yelling]
And it's the last time.
Because you're not gonna
make it outta here alive.
[LUCY] Even as the Bane
Particles eat away at him,
Laxus faces his foe,
powered solely by the spirit
of vengeance for his friends.
But Tempester is known
as "The Immortal."
Could this really be true?
Our Lightning Dragon
Slayer is definitely
gonna test that theory.
Meanwhile, as Erza locates
the demolished control room,
she also finds another life
or death battle with Kyoka.
The showdown with the Demon
Gates enters its final phase,
with humanity on the line.
Next Time: "Tartaros
Chapter Final Duels."
This is the
beginning of the end.