- Makarov:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
- Happy: AY, SIR!
THIS YEAR'S S-CLASS
WIZARD PROMOTION TRIAL
STARTED OFF WITH A BANG.
- Natsu: ERZA AND MIRAJANE
BOTH HAD TO PASS THIS TEST
BEFORE THEY GOT TO
LEVEL UP IN THE GUILD.
I'M TOTALLY FIRED UP
ABOUT GOING BIG TIME!
- Lucy: I'M JUST GLAD
ROUND ONE'S FINALLY OVER.
- Happy: OH, MAN.
THAT WAS A SUPER HARD ONE.
- Natsu: SO WHAT'S THE SECOND
ROUND GONNA BE AGAIN?
- Lucy: WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO FIND THE GRAVE
OF FAIRY TAIL'S
FIRST MASTER, MAVIS.
- Natsu: BUT WE GOT INTERRUPTED
BY SOME CREEPY CRYBABY.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF
A BIG TEST HERE, PAL!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I WAS WONDERING
ABOUT SOMETHING.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
WHAT KIND OF MAGIC MEST USES?
- OH, YES. YOU'RE STILL
SOMEWHAT NEW TO THE GUILD.
YOU KNOW, HONESTLY,
I'M NOT SURE.
- I FIND THAT TO BE
RATHER PECULIAR.
- YES, WELL...
- HOLD ON.
ARE YOU IMPLYING
THAT THIS MEST FELLOW
MIGHT NOT ACTUALLY
BE A MEMBER OF
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD?
- ALL I CAN SAY IS THAT
THE FIRST TIME I MET HIM
I GOT A STRANGE FEELING.
SO I'VE TRIED TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT I DO AND DO NOT KNOW
ABOUT HIM.
WHAT I DO KNOW
IS CRYSTAL CLEAR.
- Carla: WHAT?
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
- Pantherlily:
WHAT I MEAN IS THIS.
I'VE BARELY SPOKEN TO HIM,
BUT THERE ARE
THINGS ABOUT HIM
I KNOW WITH COMPLETE
CERTAINTY,
AS IF I CAN SEE THEM.
HIS NAME IS MEST GRYDER.
HE'S THE EARTH LAND PUPIL
OF MY PRINCE,
WHOM YOU CALL MYSTOGAN.
HE COMPETED IN LAST YEAR'S
S-CLASS TRIAL,
BUT HE DID NOT PASS.
AND THAT'S ALL.
I FEEL AS THOUGH I SHOULD
KNOW MORE ABOUT HIM,
BUT IT'S ALL JUST A HAZE.
- I EXPLICITLY TOLD WENDY
SHE SHOULD BY NO MEANS
ASSOCIATE WITH THAT MAN.
- WELL, WE CAN'T
CHANGE THAT NOW,
BUT HOPEFULLY
OUR FEARS ARE UNFOUNDED.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
FLOWERS LIKE THESE BEFORE.
THEY'RE SO PRETTY,
YOU SEE?
( gasps )
( screams )
- I MUST KNOW.
I MUST FIND OUT
WHAT THESE NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN
FLOWERS TASTE LIKE.
- BUT THE FLOWERS
ARE FOR LOOKING AT.
THEY'RE NOT FOR EATING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
NATSU?
I THOUGHT WE WERE
GONNA GO TO THE TOP.
- THERE'S SOMETHING I'VE GOTTA
DO FIRST, LITTLE BUDDY.
I GOTTA FIND THAT
TEARY-EYED JERK
THAT MESSED UP THE SCARF
THAT IGNEEL GAVE ME
AND REALLY GIVE HIM
SOMETHING TO CRY ABOUT.
- HOW ARE WE GONNA LOOK FOR HIM
AND LOOK FOR MAVIS' GRAVE
AT THE SAME TIME?
IT'D BE A LOT EASIER
IF YOU JUST PICK ONE.
- IT'LL BE WAY FASTER
TO DO THEM BOTH AT ONCE!
- I DON'T THINK IT'S
GONNA WORK THAT WAY.
- ( clucking )
- WHY ARE YOU CREEPS
EVEN HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- ( chuckles )
WE HAVE COME HERE
IN ORDER TO HUNT DOWN
ALL THE FAIRIES!
- ( gasps )
- Happy: IRON SOUL.
- THAT'S SO LOUD!
IT'S KILLING MY EARS!
HE'S USING MAGIC WRITING.
THAT'S JUST LIKE
WHAT YOU DO.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT?
HEY, LEVY!
- I'M ALMOST POSITIVE THAT
HE'S USING THE EASTERN VERSION
OF SOLID SCRIPT MAGIC.
( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- GAJEEL!
HE'S COMING RIGHT FOR US.
HE CAN'T HEAR ME.
- ( squawks )
- ( gasps )
- ARE THOSE EGGS?
( gasps )
- EGG BUSTER!
- ( groans )
( grunts, gasps )
- ( grunts )
- Gajeel: OH, MAN.
I COULDN'T HEAR HIM COMING
OVER ALL THE DANG NOISE.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- GAJEEL!
( screams )
SOLID SCRIPT!
SILENT!
- ( squawks )
- SHE TURNED DOWN
THE VOLUME ON YOU.
- HOW DARE THAT
INSOLENT LITTLE GIRL
ERASE WHAT I HAVE WRITTEN.
- MY TURN.
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
( clucking )
- NOW, FIRE!
- ( squawks )
- SLIDE, SLIDE, SLIDE, SLIDE.
YOU SHALL PAY!
( grunts )
SLICE!
ZUBABABA!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
SLICE!
ZUBABABA!
- ( grunts )
( panting )
MAN...
THIS GUY IS INTENSE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( squawks )
( grunts )
- FIRE.
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM.
( screams )
- NO, LEVY!
( gasps )
- ( shouts )
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HE'S ACTUALLY CUTTING
THROUGH MY SCALES.
- ( grunts )
PIERCE!
( groans )
- KASHA.
NOW MY DARK SWORD TECHNIQUE.
- ( grunts )
NO.  PLEASE STOP.
- NARUKAMI!
- ( gasps )
- SLICE SLICE SLICE SLICE!
SLICE!
JAKI.
- ( screams )
- GAJEEL!
- ( grunts )
- GAJEEL?
- IF THE REST OF THE GUILD
ARE AS WEAK AS THESE TWO,
WE VERY WELL MAY
DISPOSE OF THEM ALL
BEFORE THE MAIN FORCE ARRIVES.
- LET'S TAKE THEM ALL DOWN.
- ( grunts )
THERE'S MORE OF YOU
SCUMBAGS?
- THIS ONE'S STILL
CLUCKING AWAY.
- ( chuckles ) WE'RE MERELY
THE RECONNAISSANCE TEAM.
THE REST OF GRIMOIRE HEART
WILL BE ARRIVING SHORTLY.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT?
THE REST OF THE GUILD?
- Gajeel: LEVY, RUN.
- ( gasps )
- THIS AIN'T GONNA BE
SOME SIMPLE LITTLE FIGHT.
IT'LL BE WORSE
THAN WE CAN IMAGINE.
- BUT I CAN'T JUST LEAVE YOU.
- GET OUT OF HERE!
YOU GOTTA TELL
THE OTHERS WHAT'S GOING ON.
I'LL BE OKAY.
I CAN HANDLE THESE GUYS,
SO MOVE IT!
- ( crying )
- YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WHAT'D I JUST TELL YOU, LEVY?
NOW GET MOVING!
THAT'S IRON.
- Levy: STAY STRONG, PLEASE.
- ( grunts )
- HUH.  HOW UNFORTUNATE.
WE LET THE LITTLE GIRL ESCAPE.
- THAT ONE'S GOT
QUITE A BIT OF PLUCK.
HUNTING HER DOWN WILL BE
EVEN MORE FUN.
- ( both gasp )
- YOU THINK YOU WANT TO GO
TO WAR WITH FAIRY TAIL, DO YOU?
- ( gasps )
HE HAS THE STRENGTH TO STAND?
- I DID TOO.
WAY BACK WHEN.
- MESSING WITH FAIRY TAIL
IS THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
YOU'VE EVER MADE!
- ( chuckles )
ARE YOU READY?
YOU'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT
JUST HOW BAD YOU SCREWED UP.
- ( Levy panting )
I'VE GOT TO LET EVERYBODY KNOW
WE'RE IN BIG TROUBLE.
GRIMOIRE HEART IS GONNA
BE HERE ANY MINUTE NOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THEY WANT FROM US,
BUT THINGS ARE ABOUT
TO GET REALLY SCARY.
( gasps )
( grunting )
( groans )
HOLD ON, GAJEEL.
- IRON DRAGON ROAR!
- DEFENSE.
- ( squawks )
- ( gasps )
- ( clucking )
- WHAT IN THE--?
- LOOK ABOVE YOUR HEAD,
YOU FOOL.
- ( gasps )
- HEAVY EGG RAIN!
- ( grunts )
HUH?
( grunting )
- SHUBABABABABA!
- ( straining )
KEEP DREAMING, BUDDY.
THAT DULL LITTLE
POCKET KNIFE YOU GOT
AIN'T CUTTING
THROUGH MY STEEL!
( grunts )
- ( squawks )
- STOP YOUR CLUCKING.
- PIERCE!
- ( gasps )
- I WILL RUN YOU
RIGHT THROUGH.
WHAT?
- ( grunts )
( chuckles )
LOSING AIN'T
AN OPTION FOR ME.
- ( grunts )
DAMN IT.
- YOU HEAR ME?
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN!
- Erza: LEVY, WAKE UP.
LEVY!
- HOW'D YOU MANAGE
TO GET SUCH AWFUL INJURIES?
- IT'S YOU.
THANK GOODNESS.
- MY WORD,
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE.
AND HE NEEDS HELP.
- ( grunting )
- ( chuckles )
- ( screams )
TAKING ON FAIRY TAIL
LIKE THIS...
THESE IDIOTS ARE JUST
AS THICK-HEADED AS I WAS.
- Narrator: GAJEEL WAS ONCE PART
OF ANOTHER LESS FRIENDLY GUILD
KNOWN AS PHANTOM LORD.
THEY SUCCEEDED IN DESTROYING
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD HALL
AND EVEN TAKING LUCY PRISONER.
THEY CAME VERY CLOSE TO
WIPING OUT FAIRY TAIL FOREVER.
LUCKILY THEY WERE DEFEATED
IN THE NICK OF TIME
AND THE GUILD WAS DISBANDED.
THE WIZARDS WHO WERE ONCE
PART OF THAT BAND OF HOOLIGANS
WENT THEIR SEPARATE WAYS
AND BEGAN NEW LIVES ELSEWHERE.
HOWEVER...
- ( groans )
- HEY THERE.
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE MASTER MAKAROV.
- ( chuckles )
- ( sighs )
SO DID YOU COME HERE
TO GLOAT?
- ( grunts )
WHAT A NICE HELLO INDEED.
NOT BIG ON MANNERS,
ARE YOU?
YOUR FRIEND JUVIA IS
THE NEWEST MEMBER OF OUR GUILD.
- YOU KIDDING ME?
- NO, SIR.
SHE WAS VERY CONCERNED
ABOUT YOUR WELL-BEING
AFTER ALL THAT HAPPENED.
- CHICK'S GOT
RAIN FOR BRAINS.
WHAT IS SHE THINKING?
( sighs )
- HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT
WHAT YOUR NEXT MOVE IS?
- MY NEXT MOVE?
I DON'T KNOW JUST YET.
KEEPING MY OPTIONS OPEN,
I GUESS.
- ( sighs )
I HAVE ANOTHER
QUESTION FOR YOU.
- SO, SHOOT.
- WHEN YOU REFLECT ON IT,
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY
WERE YOUR OWN REASONS
FOR GOING TO WAR
WITH FAIRY TAIL?
- HMM?
- WHAT DID BEING PART OF
PHANTOM LORD MEAN TO YOU?
FOR THAT MATTER, WHAT DID THE
IDEA OF A GUILD MEAN TO YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
WITH THE POWERS YOU POSSESS?
- ( sighs )
YOU SURE GOT A LOT OF
QUESTIONS, OLD MAN.
- THEY'RE ALL THE SAME.
WHAT KIND OF MAN DO YOU
TELL YOURSELF YOU ARE?
AND IS THAT MAN
THE SAME PERSON
WHO LIVES INSIDE
YOUR HEART?
IF JOSE ASKED IT OF YOU,
WOULD YOU TAKE
A LIFE FOR HIM?
IS HIS POWER ABSOLUTE?
IS HIS EVERY WISH
YOUR COMMAND?
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN YOU'RE NOTHING MORE
THAN HIS PUPPET.
BUT I DON'T GET THAT IMPRESSION
FROM YOU, GAJEEL.
YOU'RE NOT MINDLESS.
- WOULD YOU QUIT
FLAPPING YOUR GUMS
AND GET LOST ALREADY?
- Makarov:
THERE'S NO REASON TO GIVE UP
AND PLUNGE INTO THE DARKNESS.
- ( gasps )
- COME WITH US.
JOIN THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
- ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHY IN THE HECK WOULD I
EVER WANT TO DO THAT?
- THERE IS GREAT VALUE
IN THE TIME SPENT
IN ONES OWN COMPANY,
BUT A LIFETIME OF
TOTAL ISOLATION
IS A FATE NO ONE
SHOULD ENDURE.
- ( gasps )
YOU KNOW I'M THE ONE WHO
TRASHED YOUR GUILD HALL, RIGHT?
- OH, I KNOW.
WE'LL REBUILD IT.
- AND I WAS ALSO THE ONE
WHO HURT YOUR THREE
LITTLE FRIENDS.
- I KNOW.
A DESPICABLE ACT THAT I WILL
NEVER COMPLETELY FORGIVE.
BUT FOR ME,
LETTING A YOUNG MAN
FALL INTO DARKNESS
WHEN I KNOW I COULD HAVE
DONE SOMETHING TO PREVENT IT
IS SOMETHING EVEN MORE
UNFORGIVEABLE.
- ( gasping )
- I CANNOT GUARANTEE
TOTAL SALVATION.
I CAN MERELY POINT YOU
DOWN A PATH OUT OF THE SHADOWS.
WILL YOU CHOOSE
TO WALK THAT PATH,
OR TO FOREGO IT
AND REMAIN WHERE YOU ARE?
- I WILL.
- WHAT?!
- ( grunting )
I WILL NOT BE DEFEATED.
NOT GONNA HAPPEN!
I'LL NEVER LOSE TO
SCUM LIKE YOU.
BECAUSE...
I'M A FAIRY TAIL WIZARD.
( grunts )
- NO.  NOT MY KITANA.
MY SOUL IS IN
THAT BLADE!
- DRAGON SLAYER SECRET ART.
- ( gasps )
- KARMIC DEMON...
- ( screams )
- IRON GOD SWORD!
( grunts )
- ( chirping )
- ( grunts )
- GAJEEL!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- ( gasps ) THERE HE IS.
- ( panting )
GAJEEL.  OH, PLEASE TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
- ( grunts )
TOLD YOU I COULD HANDLE THOSE
CHUMPS BY MYSELF, DIDN'T I?
- ( sighs )
YEAH, YOU DID.
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- YOU FOOLS DON'T
STAND A CHANCE.
OUR MAIN FIGHTING FORCE
IS RIGHT ON OUR HEELS.
WIZARDS WHOSE POWER
FAR EXCEEDS MY OWN.
THEY ARE KNOWN AS
THE SEVEN KIN OF PURGATORY.
( laughs )
- ( gasps )
- THE SEVEN KIN ARE COMING?
- WE MUST PUT THE TRIAL ON HOLD.
RIGHT NOW,
PREPARE FOR BATTLE!
CONDITION RED!
WE SHALL INTERCEPT THEM
AT ONCE.
- WHAT?  AN ENEMY ATTACK?
WHO DARES INVADE
OUR SACRED GROUND?
- A RED FLARE?
BUT WHY?
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
- ENEMIES SIGHTED.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE S-CLASS TRIAL, HUH?
- OBVIOUSLY IT WILL HAVE TO
BE PUT ON HOLD FOR NOW.
- HMM.
I BET ITS GOT
SOMETHING TO DO WITH HIM.
THAT BIG CRYBABY.
- NAH, I DON'T THINK SO.
A RED FLARE MEANS
AN ENEMY IS COMING.
THERE MUST BE
SOMEBODY ELSE ON THE WAY.
- WELL, WHOEVER IT IS,
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR A FIGHT.
SO I SAY WE GIVE THEM
WHAT THEY CAME HERE FOR.
THAT'LL TEACH THEM
NOT TO MESS WITH US.
- AYE, SIR!
- WHY DOES THIS
HAVE TO HAPPEN NOW?
- ( gasps ) - I SWORE THAT
THIS WOULD BE MY LAST TRIAL.
I'M SERIOUS.
IF I DON'T MAKE IT THIS YEAR,
I'M LEAVING
THE GUILD FOREVER.
I WON'T GIVE UP.
I'M GONNA SEE THIS THING
THROUGH TO THE VERY END.
- CANA...
- Gray: WOULD YOU TAKE IT DOWN
A NOTCH? - ( gasps )
- EVERYONE FEELS
THE SAME WAY YOU DO.
- WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
- YEAH, NO KIDDING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WE'VE KIND OF BEEN FOL--
- IT'S JUST A COINCIDENCE, OKAY?
BUT THAT'S NOT
IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW.
IF WE'RE REALLY UNDER ATTACK,
THEN WE GOTTA FOCUS ON THAT.
- ( grunts )
LET'S GET TO
THE EMERGENCY RENDEZVOUS.
WE NEED TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING FIRST.
- ( sighs )
AS IF THE TRIAL
WASN'T HARD ENOUGH.
- ( sighs )
- SO NOW WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
- FIRST THING WE NEED TO DO
IS LOCATE MEST AND WENDY.
I'M AFRAID THEY
MAY BE LOST
AND UNABLE TO FIND
OUR BASE CAMP.
- I'LL TAKE GAJEEL
AND MEET YOU THERE IN A BIT.
- YES.
THANK YOU, LEVY.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PUSH YOURSELF
ON MY ACCOUNT,
SMALL FRY.
- Levy: WELL, I DON'T SEE YOU
GETTING THERE ON YOUR OWN,
YOU BIG LUG.
- Gajeel: YEAH YEAH.
DON'T RUB IT IN.
- Juvia: I'M SURE
MY BELOVED GRAY
NEEDS MY SUPPORT AS WELL.
- YOU THERE, SPEAK.
TELL ME WHY YOU'VE
COME TO THIS PLACE.
- ( scoffs ) REVEALING THAT
WILL DO ME NO GOOD AT ALL.
- ( groans )
- ( grunts )
WE SEEK HIM.
THE LEGENDARY BLACK WIZARD
KNOWN AS ZEREF.
- ( gasping )
- HE IS HERE ON
THIS VERY ISLAND.
- BUT THAT'S ABSURD.
- HOW CAN THAT BE TRUE?
I THOUGHT ZEREF LIVED HUNDREDS
OF YEARS AGO, DIDN'T HE?
- 400 YEARS.
- YOU FOOL.
ZEREF IS LONG SINCE DEAD.
THAT'S WHO JELLAL WAS
TRYING TO REVIVE.
- NO, HE NEVER DIED.
LORD ZEREF HAS BEEN LIVING
FOR OVER 400 YEARS.
- ( gasps )
- ACCORDING TO MASTER HADES,
HE'S SIMPLY BEEN SLEEPING.
HE SAID LORD ZEREF
WAS IN A DEEP SLUMBER
THAT LASTED FOR CENTURIES.
- I FIND THIS WHOLE STORY
EXTREMELY DIFFICULT TO BELIEVE.
- ( chirps )
- ( buzzes )
- ONCE HE HAS AWAKENED
FROM HIS SLUMBER,
THE ENTIRE WORLD WILL BE
CLOAKED IN DARKNESS.
- NONSENSE! DON'T YOU KNOW THIS
ISLAND IS OUR SACRED GROUND?
THERE'S NO WAY WE'D
ALLOW IT TO BE DEFILED
BY THE FORCES OF EVIL
WITH WHOM YOU ALIGN.
- ( chuckles )
BELIEVE WHAT YOU WILL,
BUT MASTER HADES AND
THE SEVEN KIN OF PURGATORY
WILL BE ARRIVING ON
THESE SHORES VERY SOON.
AND IT WOULD BE WISE OF YOU
NOT TO TAKE THEM LIGHTLY.
THE TIME WIZARD, ULTEAR.
RUSTYROSE.
MY SUPERIOR, CAPRICO.
KAIN HIKARU.
ZANCROW.
MELDY.
AND... THERE'S ONE MORE
MEMBER I HAVEN'T MENTIONED
WHO'S ALREADY HERE.
( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- THERE'S ONE HERE NOW?
- HEY, WHAT IS THAT?
DO YOU WHAT THE RED SIGNAL
UP THERE IS SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- UHH... IT MEANS...
NOW I WANT TO KNOW! I REALLY
WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT MEANS.
- IT'S OKAY IF YOU FORGOT,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT'S GONNA HELP.
- I NEED TO ACT NOW
BEFORE THE MAIN FORCE ARRIVES.
- Wendy: ...WHEN YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY'VE BEEN.
- Carla: WENDY!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- NEVER MIND THAT.
JUST GET AWAY FROM HIM.
ALL RIGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU CUT THE ACT
AND TELL US WHO
YOU REALLY ARE?
- HUH? WHAT THE HECK
DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
I'M MYSTOGAN'S PUPIL,
REMEMBER?
- I FIND IT HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT MY PRINCE
WOULD TAKE ON A PUPIL
IN THIS WORLD.
NOW YOU ARE SMART ENOUGH
TO USE SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE
TO BACK UP YOUR STORY.
BUT ARE YOU GONNA BE SMART
ENOUGH TO TELL US THE TRUTH?
WHO ARE YOU?
AND WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO HIDE?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS PLACE IS CRAWLING WITH
A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
- Happy: THAT EMBLEM,
THEY'RE FROM GRIMOIRE HEART.
BUT WHAT'S A DARK GUILD
DOING ON TENROU ISLAND?
- Natsu: OOH, MAYBE THIS
IS PART OF THE S-CLASS
THINGY WE'RE DOING.
YOU KNOW, LIKE A STRENGTH
TESTING FESTIVAL.
- Happy: WHO THROWS
THAT KIND OF FESTIVAL?
ANYWAY, THIS IS A TRIAL,
YOU BONEHEAD, REMEMBER?
- Natsu and Happy:
NEXT TIME, "MAKAROV CHARGES."
- Natsu: HEY, MAN. A FESTIVAL
WHERE WE BEAT UP BAD GUYS
WHO ARE TRYING TO
MESS UP OUR TRIAL
SOUNDS LIKE FUN TO ME.
- Happy: I THINK WE HAVE
DIFFERENT IDEAS
ABOUT WHAT'S CONSIDERED
"FUN."