( dramatic music plays )
- ( theme music plays )
- ( man sings in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTASY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP
WITH A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- Soldier:
IT'S BEEN CONFIRMED.
THE HUMANS HAVE ATTACHED THE
SO-CALLED "DRAGON CHAIN CANNON"
TO THE FLOATING ISLAND HOLDING
THE LACRIMA, WITH THE INTENT
OF EMPLOYING IT AS A BOMB
AGAINST EXTALIA.
REGRETFULLY, I MUST ALSO REPORT
THAT SIR NICHIYA
AND HIS BATTALION HAVE BEEN
TRANSFORMED INTO LACRIMA.
THEY ARE CURRENTLY BEING
HELD HOSTAGE.
EXTALIA IS IN GRAVE DANGER.
- THIS IS AN OUTRAGE.
- BARBARISM AT ITS FINEST.
- I NEVER THOUGHT THE HUMANS
WOULD RESORT TO SUCH METHODS.
- Soldier: ADDITIONALLY,
A FALLEN AND A HUMAN HAVE COME
TO TOWN URGING EVERYONE
TO ABANDON THEIR HOMES
AND EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
THE CITIZENS HAVE DISSOLVED
INTO A MOB.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE US DO,
MY QUEEN?
- I WILL DEAL WITH THIS MATTER
PERSONALLY.
- YOUR HIGHNESS.
- YOU CANNOT BE SERIOUS.
- WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO,
YOUR MAJESTY?
- IT'S TIME TO END THE CHARADE.
- GAJEEL.  QUICK!
USE YOUR DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC
TO SHATTER THE LACRIMA
AND TURN EVERYONE BACK.
- CAN'T.
NO TIME FOR THAT NOW.
THIS PUPPY'S SPEEDING UP.
- OH, NO!
- COME ON, LET'S GO!
IF WE CAN'T STOP IT,
EVERYONE WE KNOW WILL DIE.
- GIVE IT EVERYTHING
YOU'VE GOT.
- THIS WON'T WORK.  IT'S GOT
TOO MUCH MASS AND MOMENTUM.
- IF WE FALL, WE'LL DO SO
WITH THE REST OF MAGNOLIA.
- DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL SAVE YOU GUYS.
- ( screaming )
OUT OF MY WAY!
- NATSU.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN--
- HUH?
GIVE ME A HAND, BUDDY,
WOULD YOU?
- AYE, SIR.
- ALL RIGHT, TEMPORARY TRUCE,
FURBALL.
- DON'T RUN FROM ME.
- WE'LL FINISH THIS.
JUST LET ME STOP THIS THING
FIRST.  THEN I'LL BEAT YOU.
- YOU CAN'T.  IMBECILE.
ONCE IT'S BEGUN,
THERE'S NO WAY TO STOP IT.
THIS IS THE END.
EDOLAS IS ABOUT
TO CHANGE FOREVER
AND NONE OF US WILL LIVE
TO SEE THE AFTERMATH.
- WRONG.  WE AIN'T DYING.
WHEN THIS IS OVER WITH,
YOU'RE COMING TO FAIRY TAIL.
YOU'LL BE MY CAT, EVEN IF I HAVE
TO DRAG YOU THERE. ( laughs )
- THEY'RE STILL GONNA COLLIDE.
- NO!
- GIVE IT ALL YOU'VE GOT.
- ( screaming )
IT'S NOT GONNA END THIS WAY!
DON'T GIVE UP.  WE CAN
STILL PUSH THIS THING BACK.
- AYE, SIR.
- ( grunting )
GAJEEL, WHY ARE YOU DOWN HERE?
YOU SHOULD BE USING YOUR MAGIC
TO TURN THE OTHERS BACK TO
NORMAL.  GET BACK UP THERE.
- IF YOU WANNA DEAL WITH
THE BLACK CAT, BE MY GUEST.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO WORRY
ABOUT THE LACRIMA OR THE CAT
SO JUST PUSH.
- WE HAVE TO STOP IT
OR EVERYONE FROM MAGNOLIA
WILL BE LOST FOREVER.
- COCO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- LILY.  OH, YOU'RE STILL
IN ONE PIECE.  I'M GLAD.
WHO NEEDS ETERNAL MAGIC POWER
WHEN YOU CAN HAVE
ETERNAL SMILES?
- WHAT KIND OF NONSENSE IS THAT?
YOU HAVE TO GET OUT
OF HERE, COCO.
THESE PEOPLE CAN'T STOP
EXTALIA'S DESTRUCTION.
- DON'T BE SO SURE.
IF THERE'S ONE THING FAIRY
TAIL WIZARDS ALWAYS PROVE,
IT'S THAT NOTHING'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( grunting )
AYE, AYE, SIR.
- LUCKY, WHAT IS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IF IT RUINS MY CROPS,
THERE'LL BE HELL TO PAY.
- THE ROYAL ARMY
IS ATTACKING US.
- THEY CAN'T REALLY BE STUPID
ENOUGH TO REVOLT.
- THEY MUST NOT KNOW
OUR QUEEN'S TRUE POWER.
- I BET THE QUEEN'S GONNA USE
HER MAGIC ANY MINUTE NOW.
THE HUMANS ARE GONNA PAY.
- SHE BETTER DO IT SOON.
- NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
THE QUEEN WILL PUNISH
OUR ENEMIES.
- IT LOOKS LIKE THE LACRIMA
HIT THE ISLAND.
- IF THAT WERE THE CASE, I DOUBT
WE'D BE AROUND TO DISCUSS IT.
- I'M SO SORRY, CARLA.
THERE'S NOTHING WE COULD DO.
- THIS ISN'T OVER YET.
WE'RE NOT GIVING UP THAT EASILY.
- PLEASE LISTEN, EVERYONE.
- SO YOU'RE STILL HERE?
I'LL FIX THAT.
- OH!
- SIR NADI.
- CARLA.
- SIR,
THROWING ROCKS IS DANGEROUS.
SOMEBODY COULD GET HURT.
- YEAH, BUT SHE'S A FALLEN,
SO IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
- DON'T YOU REALIZE
WHAT'S HAPPENED?
THEY RISKED THEIR OWN SAFETY
TO WARN US OF THE DANGER.
WE FIND OURSELVES IN THIS MESS
BECAUSE WE IGNORED THEM.
- YOU'VE LOST YOUR MIND, NADI.
- WE DON'T NEED THEIR HELP.
THE QUEEN'S GONNA DESTROY
THAT ISLAND AND ALL THE HUMANS.
- PLEASE, YOUR HIGHNESS.
HURRY!  SAVE US!
- EVERYONE,
PLEASE CALM YOURSELVES.
- SET ASIDE YOUR FEAR, NADI.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S THE QUEEN!
- WE'RE SAVED AT LAST.
- PRAISE HER.
- ALL HAIL HER MAJESTY.
- THAT'S REALLY HER?
- THANK YOU, BUT THIS IS NOT
THE TIME TO LOWER YOUR HEADS.
NOW THAT YOU'VE CALMED DOWN,
PLEASE LISTEN
TO WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
- ANY IDEA WHY THE QUEEN WOULD
COME OUT OF HER CASTLE?
- PROBABLY SO WE CAN WATCH HER
USE HER AWESOME POWERS.
- SHUT YOUR TRAPS.
- EXTALIA IS TEETERING ON
THE EDGE OF TOTAL ANNIHILATION
THIS FATE MAY BE INESCAPABLE
FOR THE EXCEEDS.
AFTER MUCH SOUL SEARCHING,
I HAVE COME TO A FINAL DECISION
ON THE MATTER.
- YOU'RE GONNA DESTROY
THE HUMANS FIRST, RIGHT?
- BE QUIET AND LISTEN.
- ( gasps )
- WAIT, YOUR HIGHNESS, WHY ARE
YOU TAKING OFF YOUR ROBES?
- I HAVE DECIDED THAT IT IS TIME
FOR YOU TO FINALLY BE TOLD
THE TRUTH ABOUT YOUR QUEEN.
I AM JUST AN ORDINARY EXCEED,
NOT WORTHY OF YOUR WORSHIP
AS A QUEEN OR AS A GOD.
I'M NO BETTER THAN
THE REST OF YOU.
- NO, IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
- I'M SO SORRY,
BUT I DO NOT POSSESS THE POWER
TO FIGHT THE HUMANS.
AS YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE,
I WAS BORN WITH ONE WING.
FOR EXCEEDS, OUR MAGIC POWER
IS SYMBOLIZED BY OUR WINGS,
OR AERA, AND TWO WINGS
SIGNIFY ONE'S CONTROL
OF TRUE MAGIC POWER.
I LACK THAT POWER.
MY MAGIC IS WEAK.
I CAN NEVER ATONE
FOR MY DECEPTION.
YOUR NAMES ARE MISS WENDY
AND MISS CARLA, CORRECT?
MY DEEPEST APOLOGIES
TO YOU, AS WELL.
THIS IS ENTIRELY MY FAULT.
SO PLEASE DO NOT HARBOR
ANY ILL WILL TOWARDS
THOSE GATHERED HERE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
- NO, THE BLAME RESTS
WITH THOSE OF US WHO DARED
TO CONCOCT THE IDEA OF
AN EXCEED QUEEN TO BEGIN WITH,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
WE EXCEED HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
SMALLER AND WEAKER THAN HUMANS.
THEY TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF THAT FACT
AND DID TERRIBLE THINGS TO US
WHENEVER THEY GOT THE CHANCE.
SO TO PROTECT OURSELVES, WE MADE
HUMANS BELIEVE WE WERE DIVINE
AND CREATED AN ALL-POWERFUL
QUEEN TO SERVE AS THE EMBODIMENT
OF OUR MIGHT.
- Muganto: WE HAD TO RAISE THE
FRAGILE SPIRITS OF OUR PEOPLE.
SO WE REVEALED THE QUEEN
TO EXTALIA, AND CONVINCED THEM
THAT SHE POSSESSED
THE ALMIGHTY POWER OF A GOD.
- BUT HER DIVINE POWER
WAS AN ELABORATE BLUFF,
MAINTAINED BY A SELECT FEW
WHO WERE PRIVY TO THE TRUTH.
- Martam: IT TOOK SOME TIME,
BUT EVENTUALLY THE HUMANS WERE
SO TERRIFIED OF THE QUEEN'S
FICTIONAL POWERS,
THEY WOULDN'T EVEN LOOK AT
AN EXCEED FOR FEAR OF HER WRATH.
THE MOST PREVALENT
OF THEIR FEARS WAS THE IDEA
THAT SHE CHOOSES
WHICH HUMANS SHOULD BE KILLED.
IN TRUTH, NEITHER THE QUEEN
NOR ANY OF US
HAVE EVER POSSESSED THE POWER
TO DECIDE WHETHER ANOTHER BEING
WILL LIVE OR DIE.
THE ONLY THING WE HAVE
IS CHAGOT'S ABILITY TO SEE
INTO AN INDIVIDUAL'S
IMMEDIATE FUTURE.
SHE CAN SEE WHEN
A PERSON WILL DIE.
WE TOOK ADVANTAGE OF THAT POWER,
AND MADE THE HUMANS BELIEVE
THAT PEOPLE PERISHED
ACCORDING TO HER WILL.
- ( crying )
NO, THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
- WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- OUR QUEEN IS A GOD.
THERE'S NO WAY SHE'S NOT.
- STOP LYING AND DEFEAT
THE HUMANS BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- DECEITFUL NONSENSE.
- CARLA!
- WHETHER YOU HAVE POWER
OR NOT MEANS NOTHING TO ME.
WHAT MATTERS IS THAT YOU ORDERED
MY FRIENDS TO BE KILLED.
THAT IS AN UNDENIABLE FACT.
- CHAGOT GAVE NO SUCH ORDERS.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN THE HUMANS
EXPLOITING THE LEGEND
OF THE QUEEN'S POWER--
- BE QUIET!
YOU PLANTED FALSE MEMORIES
AND ORDERED ME
TO SLAUGHTER MY CLOSEST FRIEND.
UNTIL A FEW DAYS AGO,
I'D NEVER EVEN SEEN MY HOMELAND.
YOU TOOK MY LIFE FROM ME.
- I'M SORRY.
- WAIT, IT'S AN INCREDIBLY LONG
AND COMPLICATED STORY.
- YOUR EXCUSES WON'T HELP
THE DAMAGE THAT'S BEEN DONE.
- Wendy: I DON'T THINK THIS
IS THE TIME TO FOCUS ON THAT.
- ( gasping )
- Queen: YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY
CORRECT, CARLA.
MY SINS ARE MANY AND YOUR
SUFFERING IS AMONG THEM.
YOU'VE DONE NOTHING,
YET I'VE PUT YOU THROUGH MORE
PAIN THAN ANYONE.
- NO, YOUR HIGHNESS.
- TO ATONE, YOU PERSONALLY
CARRY OUT MY PUNISHMENT.
PLEASE,
PUNISH ME FOR MY CRIMES.
AS A FRIEND TO BOTH HUMANS
AND EXCEEDS,
YOU MORE THAN ANYONE HAVE
THE RIGHT TO CARRY IT OUT.
- CARLA.
- MY QUEEN, YOU CAN'T DIE.
- WE FORGIVE YOU, YOUR MAJESTY.
- NOW, PLEASE.  EVERYONE
SHOULD LEAVE IMMEDIATELY
I WILL JOIN EXTALIA IN ITS RUIN.
YOU MUST LIVE ON AND THRIVE.
- STOP!
YOU CAN'T GO THROUGH WITH THIS.
- ( crying )
- I DON'T WANNA LEAVE.
- YEAH.
- I'M STAYING HERE, TOO.
- THE EXCEED WILL VANISH
INTO HISTORY NOW.
- THAT'S WHY THE QUEEN DECIDED
TO REVEAL EVERYTHING.
- IF HER MAJESTY'S STAYING HERE,
THEN SO AM I.
- I'LL STAY WITH YOU TILL
THE END, YOUR HIGHNESS.
- SAVE YOURSELVES AND ALLOW ME
TO BEAR THIS PUNISHMENT ALONE.
- CARLA, NO!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
HOW CAN YOU GIVE UP SO EASILY?
THIS IS YOUR HOMELAND,
ISN'T IT?
DO YOU SERIOUSLY NEED A GOD
OR QUEEN TO GET ANYTHING DONE?
YOU'VE HELD ON FOR DEAR LIFE
ALL THIS TIME,
EVEN IF IT MEANT RESORTING
TO LIES.
AFTER ALL THAT, YOU'RE JUST
GOING TO LIE DOWN AND DIE?
IT'S OKAY IF YOU'RE WEAK.
IF YOU ALL WORK TOGETHER,
THERE IS NO LIMIT
TO WHAT YOU CAN ACCOMPLISH.
EXTALIA CAN'T DISAPPEAR.
I'VE FINALLY COME HOME.
AFTER ALL THIS, I CAN'T
LET IT BE DESTROYED.
I'M GOING TO SAVE EXTALIA
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
- CARLA!
- RIGHT.  I'M GOING TO
DO EVERYTHING I CAN.
- NADI.
- BECAUSE I'M A CITIZEN
OF EXTALIA.
- ( screaming )
- IT'S GETTING
PRETTY TIGHT HERE.
- ( grunting )
- JUST KEEP PUSHING, GUYS.
- USE EVERY OUNCE
OF POWER YOU GOT LEFT.
- THEY MUST BE MAD.
DO THEY HONESTLY BELIEVE THAT
THEIR HUMAN STRENGTH ALONE
CAN PREVENT THIS MASSACRE?
- CARLA, IT'S YOU.
- I'M NOT GIVING UP.
I'LL PROTECT FAIRY TAIL
AND EXTALIA.
I CAN'T JUST WATCH
MY HOMES BE DESTROYED.
- ( screaming )
- HUH?
- WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- BECAUSE I WANT TO PROTECT
MY HOME AS WELL.
YOUR COURAGE INSPIRED ME.
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THEY ALL CAME.
- EXCEEDS AREN'T AFRAID TO
PROTECT OUR LAND WITH OUR PAWS.
- THIS IS FOR OUR BELOVED QUEEN,
WHO WAS WILLING TO GIVE HER
OWN LIFE TO PROTECT EXTALIA
AND ITS CITIZENS.
- AND FOR WENDY AND CARLA,
WHO RISKED THEIR LIVES
TO SAVE US FROM OURSELVES.
- HERE GOES.  EVERYONE GET READY
TO PUSH WITH ALL YOUR MIGHT.
- CHAGOT,
YOUR WING IS TOO FRAGILE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
- NO.  MY FATE WILL BE
THE SAME AS MY PEOPLE.
WE SURVIVE OR FALL AS ONE.
- MA, I THINK I'M HALLUCINATING.
- EVERYONE IN EXTALIA
HAS COME TOGETHER.
- LILY, WHAT POSSESSED YOU
TO SAVE A HUMAN CHILD?
- IF I HADN'T,
HE WOULD HAVE PERISHED.
- HOW FOOLISH.  YOU BROUGHT
SUCH RABBLE INTO EXTALIA.
IT TURNS MY STOMACH.
- I CANNOT IGNORE ANY CREATURE
WHO HAS BEEN SERIOUSLY WOUNDED.
- HAVE THE RULES OF OUR QUEEN
COMPLETELY SLIPPED YOUR MIND?
- YOU'RE HEREBY DEEMED A FALLEN
AND EXILED FROM EXTALIA FOREVER.
- EXILED?
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DON'T FEEL GUILTY.
YOU'RE NOT TO BLAME FOR MY
PEOPLE'S SHORTSIGHTEDNESS.
NOW THE FIRST THING IS GET
YOU BACK TO YOUR HOMELAND.
- YOUR MAJESTY!
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps ) PANTHERLILY.
- ( laughs )
- TELL ME YOUR MAJESTY.
HAVE YOU FINALLY GROWN WEARY
OF LYING?
- I'M SO SORRY I'VE HURT YOU.
- YOU KNOW, NO MATTER
HOW MUCH I TRIED TO HATE IT,
EXTALIA IS STILL MY HOMELAND.
- LILY.
- BUT IT'S NO USE NOW.
EVEN WITH ALL THESE EXCEEDS
WORKING TOGETHER,
THERE'S NO STOPPING IT.
FORGIVE ME, PLEASE.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
IT DIDN'T HAVE TO HAPPEN.
I COULD HAVE STOPPED THE HUMANS,
BUT I DID NOTHING.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M CERTAIN THAT
YOUR WORDS WILL REACH THEM.
- JUST KEEP PUSHING!
- ( grunting )
- GIVE IT YOUR ALL, GUYS.
- PUSH.
- WE CAN DO IT!
- THIS WON'T BE THE END OF US.
- QUITTING IS NOT AN OPTION,
NOT FOR FAIRY TAIL.
- WE WILL STOP IT,
NO MATTER THE COST.
- LET'S PUSH TOO, LUCKY.
- AYE, SIR.
- ( screaming )
- AYE, SIR!
- All: AYE, SIR!
- THIS IS IT.
GIVE IT YOUR ALL!
- THEY'VE ACTUALLY PUSHED THE
LACRIMA A SAFE DISTANCE AWAY.
- WHAT NOW?
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps )
DID WE WIN?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- THE LACRIMA.
- IT DISAPPEARED.
DOES THAT MEAN--
- WHAT HAPPENED TO ALL
OF OUR FRIENDS?
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE--
- Mystogan: DON'T WORRY
THEY'RE ALL SAFE AND SOUND.
- Erza: MYSTOGAN.
- SORRY, BUT FINDING
AN ADEQUATE ANIMA VESTIGE
TO RESTORE EVERYTHING TOOK
A BIT LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
WITHOUT YOUR EFFORTS, I NEVER
WOULD HAVE MADE IT IN TIME.
YOU HAVE MY GRATITUDE.
- ( laughs )
- EVERYBODY'S BACK TO NORMAL?
- YES.
BY PASSING THROUGH
THE ANIMA AGAIN,
THE LACRIMA WILL RETURN TO ITS
ORIGINAL FORM IN EARTH LAND.
IT'S FINALLY OVER.
- WE REALLY DID IT?
- WELL, I'LL BE.
WE SAVED EXTALIA
WITH OUR VERY OWN PAWS.
- ( laughing )
- ( cheering )
- GREAT JOB, EVERYBODY.
- LILY.
LONG AGO, YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
I'M GLAD THAT I COULD RETURN
THE FAVOR TODAY.
- YES,
AND I COULDN'T BEGIN
TO THANK YOU,
MY PRINCE.
- OUR LONG LOST PRINCE
IS HOME AT LAST.
- HE'S WHAT?
- ( gasps, screaming )
- ( all gasp )
- NO, NOT MY CAT.
- LILY!
- WE'RE NOT DONE HERE.
DESTROY EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
- ( theme music playing )
- Natsu: HAPPY, LOOK.
THERE'S SOME KIND OF
FAKE DRAGON THING HERE.
WHAT DID THAT CRAZY
DAPHNE LADY CALL IT?
A HEMORRHOID?
- Happy: "DRAGONOID," DOOFUS.
BUT THIS THING LOOKS DIFFERENT
THAN DAPHNE'S MONSTER.
- IT'S JUST ANOTHER DRAGON
WANNABE.
I'LL TRASH IT LIKE THE LAST ONE
AND CALL IT A DAY.
- I DON'T LIKE HOW THIS THING
JUST CAME OUT OF NOWHERE.
IT'S FISHY.
- WHAT THE HECK?  MY MAGIC ISN'T
WORKING ON THIS THING.
- WHOA!
IT'S CHANGING COLORS.
- THIS ISN'T A DRAGON HUNT.
IT'S A CHAMELEON HUNT.