Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
[PORLYUSICA] She's
mastered one of them?
And at such a young age!
Here it comes!
Yeah!
Wendy learned a
secret technique?
A really strong one, too!
She's quite resourceful.
What are you doing now?
Are you trying to trap me?
[SHELIA]
But you're in here, too!
Shattering Light Sky Drill!
[SHELIA screams]
Shelia!
[LUCY and NATSU] Yeah!
[WENDY] I haven't fully
mastered the Milky Way yet,
but I still gave the
Sky Drill everything I had.
[WENDY]
This is my full strength.
[MATO] Oh, my.
[PORLYUSICA] Well done,
child. Well done.
[gasps]
[WENDY] I hope I didn't
overdo it. But, this means...
[MATO] I-I-It looks
like Shelia is down!
The winner of match
four is Fairy Tail--
[SHELIA] No, wait! Don't
count me out yet! Look!
I'm up! I'm up! This fight
is just getting started!
You're really somethin' else!
That was so fun!
[SHELIA]
You're not hurt, are you?
I was hoping we
could play more.
Aye, Sir! Talk about action
packed. Things are really
startin' to heat up here
at the Grand Magic Games!
After coming in eighth
place in the prelims,
Natsu and the rest
of Fairy Tail Team A
barely qualified to
participate in the tournament.
And then they did
horribly on day one.
But today is a new day,
the team's turned things around
and they've been steadily
racking up the points!
But those cretins in
Raven Tail have done
quite a number on them.
I hope Team B
can bounce back;
they're in bad shape right now.
[PANTHERLILY]
They'll have to work harder
if they want to
defeat Sabertooth.
It won't be easy. They're
the most powerful guild
in all of Fiore.
[CARLA] Like us, they have some
Dragon Slayers on their team:
Sting and Rogue.
[HAPPY] Not only that,
but they've got major skills!
Their Celestial
Spirit wizard, Yukino,
didn't do so well in her
match but everyone else
they've got is super-tough!
And then there's Raven Tail.
It turns out that
the mysterious Alexei
was actually their master, Ivan!
In case you didn't know,
he's the son of our
guild's master, Makarov,
which means he's
also Laxus's father.
Gajeel once worked
as a double agent,
by spying on Raven Tail
and reporting back
to Master Makarov.
The battle between
father-and-son guilds
seemed to go on forever,
but when it was over,
it was Wendy's turn to fight and
her opponent turned out to be...
[HAPPY] Shelia of Laymia Scale!
Did you know that
she's Sherry's cousin?
Both of you have some experience
with their guild, don't you?
I was told Laymia Scale
and Blue Pegasus
once teamed up
with Fairy Tail
to defeat the Oracion Seis.
Aye, Sir, that's true.
This festival of magic
is filled with both old
friends and new faces. In fact,
that's what makes the Grand
Magic Games so incredible!
Now! I think
it's time we get back
to the battle, don't you?
Who's gonna win this one.
Will it be Wendy or Shelia?
Go Wendy! Win it
for Fairy Tail!
Whoa, you're not
gonna give up are you?
C'mon Wendy!
She can barely stand.
Poor girl.
This is one intense battle.
[HAPPY] Small Fists!
[JELLAL] I'm not sure how,
but it's possible Shelia
could be tied in with Zeref.
[JELLAL] If that's true,
Wendy could be in real trouble!
[MALE CROWD 170B]
Hold up. That guy's...
[FEMALE CROWD 170A]
It's Mystogan!
[JELLAL] Should I try to stop
them? Or just wait and see?
[DORANBOLT] He seems
focused on Wendy.
I know they're
in the same guild,
but something's not right.
I managed to infiltrate
Fairy Tail seven years ago.
And as a result, I know some of
the guild's inside information.
[DORANBOLT] Mystogan.
There's no way he could
be in Earth Land right now.
[WENDY]
Hey, listen.
I don't hate fighting,
but I don't love it either.
It's just gonna get
worse for you if ya keep
dragging this out 'cause
it's obvious I'm gonna win.
[JELLAL] He's from the Council.
That's all I need.
[SHELIA] You should
probably just give up.
'Kay?
No, I can't!
[gasps]
The fact that I'm still standing
right here in front of you
means that I'm not backing down.
I'm willing to give everything
I've got for my guild.
I don't need your pity.
I'm not giving up, so
please, come and get me!
Beat me until I
fall to the ground!
Can ya do that?
Wendy.
[chuckles]
Well, if that's
what you really want.
It is!
Okay. Then I guess it's
time for my big attack!
[chuckles]
[SHELIA] It'll all be over
once I hit you with this one!
[SHELIA] God Slayer Secret Art!
Don't do it, Shelia!
Have you gone mad?
You dimwit! Are you trying
to kill the poor girl?
[SHELIA] She came at me full
force so I gotta do the same.
Cause that's love!
Whoa. What kind
of magic is that?
[JELLAL] No.
Gathering...
Clouds of Heaven!
Hmph.
She dodged it?
More like it missed her!
Shelia's magic can
perform self-restoration
but it's limited.
It heals physical damage.
Yet it does nothing
to recover lost stamina.
Hm.
Wendy's magic is
just the opposite.
It can't perform
self-restoration,
but it can restore
a target's stamina.
Seriously?
Uh, wait, does that mean...?
She helped her opponent,
and that's what messed her up.
So her attack was
thrown off course
because of the added power.
She made it miss.
[GRAY] By increasing
her enemy's energy!
Whoa...
[SHELIA] What a great tactic!
Way to go!
Sky Dragon Crushing Fang!
Wow, Wendy! You're awesome!
[power yell]
What an amazing turn of events,
ladies and gentlemen!
They're tough!
Neither one is giving up!
[CHAPATI] It's a small
fisted smack down!
Are they really dukin' it
out just for their guilds?
[yells]
[JELLAL] I can't stop them.
[JELLAL] Their
fists may be small...
but their spirits
are as big as the sky.
♪
Aw yeah! Let's make it a draw!
Ah! Wendy...
[ALL gasp]
Errr...!
[screaming and cheering]
[bell dinging]
[CHAPATI] You know what
that sound means! Time's up!
[CROWD cheering]
[panting]
[cheering]
And that's it, folks!
Looks like this
match ends in a draw!
[CROWD clapping and cheering]
[CHAPATI] Lamia Scale and
Fairy Tail A score five points!
That's awesome!
You were amazing,
Wendy! Good job!
They both fought splendidly.
No joke.
Those little girls are much
stronger than they look.
Yeah. That was some fight.
[sobbing]
What a match! That's gotta
be my favorite one so far!
When it comes to magic power,
Shelia's is far superior
to Wendy's, and yet...
[WENDY] Sorry. I'm probably
not what you expected.
I know I'm much smaller and
younger than most of you.
And I may not be
much of a fighter,
but I can use all kinds
of support magic. So please.
Let me join the group--
I'd be so embarrassed
if you sent me home!
[JURA] To think
that shy, little girl...
has grown into this
strong young woman.
Oh, Wendy.
Hey. What are
you crying about?
[SHELIA] I bet
that hurt. I'm sorry!
It's okay. You don't
need to apologize.
[chuckles]
[giggles]
That was a
lotta fun. Here ya go.
Feels good!
Weird as it sounds,
I kinda had fun, too.
Hey! You think you
and I could be friends?
[WENDY] Yeah. But are you sure
you want a friend like me?
Aw, c'mon! That's no way
to answer my question!
Let's be friends from
now on. Whadda ya say?
Yeah! I'd love to!
[BOTH chuckle]
[CHAPATI] Is that not the
sweetest thing you've ever seen?
The Grand Magic Games
could end right now
and I'd be a happy camper!
[YAJIMA] Hold on, we've
still got a ways to go.
It's only the end of day three.
[CHAPATI] We'll see you
tomorrow, ladies and gentlemen!
[CROWD commotion]
[JELLAL] That's odd. I thought
the ominous magic power
would dissipate once the fight
ended but I still sense it.
Perhaps Shelia isn't
the source after all.
[JELLAL] It's coming
from over there!
It's heading towards the exit!
[CROWD commotion]
[DORANBOLT] Did he notice me?
I'd better move fast.
[NARRATOR] Day three of
the Grand Magic Games
has come to an end.
The Sabertooth guild
currently holds the top spot
with thirty-four points.
They're followed
closely by Mermaid Heel,
who's in second place
with thirty-two points.
And rounding out the top three
is Laymia Scale with
thirty-one points.
The Fairy Tail teams take
fourth and fifth place,
followed by Blue Pegasus
who comes in sixth.
[MATO] I didn't expect the
Fairy Tail guild to do so well.
I'm gonna have to give
this a little thought.
[chuckles]
[JELLAL] Who's the
source of this power?
[JELLAL] Right there!
I've found you!
[JELLAL] Where'd he come from?
Going somewhere?
[JELLAL] No! Not now! They were
just right in front of me!
Tell me who you are!
[JELLAL] I could knock
him out with one hit. No.
Everyone here is
under the impression
that I'm a Fairy Tail wizard.
I can't go
attacking the Council.
[LAHAR] Doranbolt.
What's all the commotion?
[JELLAL] Damn it!
You're not fooling me.
I know that you're not Mystogan.
So who are you?
[gasps]
That was so awesome!
Don't you guys think?
Wendy put it all on the line
for us, ya know what I mean?
What a trooper!
[CROWD whispers]
I'll ask one more time.
Just who are you?
[JELLAL] I'm sorry.
I don't have time for this.
[DORANBOLT]
Hold it right there!
I know Mystogan
is not in Earth Land.
[JELLAL] I assure
you that I am.
[JELLAL] What are you--?
Let me see your face!
Man, I'm so freakin' hungry!
You're always hungry!
You should be thinkin'
about our victory,
and not stuffin' your face.
Yeah, but that's hard to do
when your stomach
keeps growlin'.
Well, Happy, I'm gonna
go find some grub.
You comin' with me?
Nope, I'm stayin' right here.
Uh. On second thought...
Hey, Wait up!
Should we follow 'em?
We might as well. We
deserve a celebratory dinner
after our performance today.
And I certainly
wouldn't mind sitting down.
Oh, no!
[gasps]
Jellal?
♪
Oh! I see that someone finally
removed your mask,
eh, Mystogan?
Yajima!
[YAJIMA] Lahar, my boy.
Now do you understand why
he has chosen to keep his face
hidden from the general public?
Mystogan's spent his
entire life dealing with
the fact that he looks
identical to Jellal.
[YAJIMA] Can you please
you show him some sympathy?
He's not... Jellal?
Tell me Lahar,
have you ever heard of
the world known as Edolas?
Yes. My men told me about it.
[YAJIMA] Then I'm sure
you're aware there is
a strong connection
to our world.
In fact everyone in Earth Land
has a twin living there.
So then... you look like him,
but that's just a coincidence?
Yes.
[BETH] That was an
amazin' match, wasn't it?
[KAGURA] Jellal...
Kagura?
[LISLIE] Whoa,
what's the matter?
Are you feelin' all right?
[BETH] Your tummy hurt?
[MILLIANNA]
Oh, no! What's wrong?
[ARAÑA] Calm down.
It'll be okay.
Hey! Somebody call a doctor!
Our friend needs help!
What happened?
She hurt or somethin'?
[gasps]
Jellal!
It's okay. I'm calm now.
He's right there! It's him!
[KAGURA] I'm well aware.
I told you I'm fine. Thanks.
They've been harboring
him all this time.
Fairy Tail's protecting Jellal?
Erzy how could you?
Thank you for
understanding my situation.
Oh, uh. No thanks needed.
I apologize for my ignorance.
Just so you know, I consider
Jellal a menace as well.
If I find him, I'll
be sure to notify you.
[JELLAL] Excuse me.
[JELLAL] I'm in
your debt, Mr. Yajima.
[YAJIMA] I won't do it again.
You should leave before you
cause any trouble for Maky.
[JELLAL] I will.
I assure you I'll be gone
by the end of the games.
That was really him.
I'll let Mr. Yajima save
face for the time being,
but just this once.
[JELLAL] The trail's gone cold.
That strange,
foreboding presence.
It can't be Zeref.
But who is it?
Hmmm.
[LAXUS] Hurts, huh?
After everything you've
done, the old geezer
still managed to have
a little faith in you.
'Cause you're his son.
Silence!
Every waking moment
I lived in the shadows
was to prepare for this day!
All so that I could finally
have the Lumen Histoire
within my grasp!
Tell me where the Lumen
Histoire is, Laxus?
Stop hiding it!
[IVAN]
You're my son, aren't you?
Where's your loyalty
to your family?
Hey geezer. Wanna tell me
about the Lumen Histoire?
Lemme guess, Ivan mentioned it?
Yeah, over and over again.
Seems he really wants
to get his hands on it.
That kid. Good for nothin'.
He tried to tell me that it's
Fairy Tail's "darkest secret."
It's not "dark" at all.
First Master!
[MAVIS] The Lumen Histoire.
It's actually what brings
light into our guild.
Remember you mustn't tell him!
Yeah, I know that.
It's top-secret information
that's only shared with...
those who serve as guild master.
Sorry. I hope you
can understand, Laxus.
Hey, as long as it
ain't somethin' weird,
I got no reason to pry.
Aw, thanks. You're the best!
I wonder...
how was Ivan able to
get hold of such
classified information?
Well, I assume...
[MAVIS] the second master,
Precht, told him.
Hmmm.
Yes, he would be
the most likely source.
I never thought that he
would fall to the dark side.
Choosing him was such
a terrible decision.
Now, now. You mustn't blame
yourself, First Master.
[MAVIS] But it's all my fault.
Ah!
I chose him.
[BOTH] Ahhh!
Please don't cry!
Uh... Hey, geezer.
What do we do?
I'm just fine!
I'm not crying! I'm not!
I'm not... crying.
Go on, Laxus!
Comfort her! Hurry!
Me? Why do I have
to do it? Can't you?
[NATSU] You gotta be kiddin' me!
Another swimsuit battle?
[HAPPY] Hey, guess what, Natsu?
I saw a pretty skimpy
lookin' bathing suit
sitting in another
guild's locker room!
[NATSU] Yeah, so?
[HAPPY] It was nothin'
but the bottoms!
Somebody's gonna
be fightin' topless!
[NATSU] Seriously?
Man, that's wild!
[HAPPY] Ugh. That's not really
the reaction I was expecting.
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next time: "Naval Battle!"
[NATSU] What kinda reaction
were you expecting?
[HAPPY] Somethin' more like,
"Heh heh, I'm gettin'
front row seats!" or
"I hope you're ready for
some jiggle, lil' buddy!"
[NATSU] Geez, I'm not a perv.