The snake charmer is
an absolutely vital part
of the zodiac.
So my true form is every bit as
majestic as that would entail.
In fact, the very place
known as the Astral Spiritus
is fully contained
within my body.
Everything that
has transpired so far
has been inside my body.
You coming here was by design,
a trap to lure you in.
[laughing evilly]
[LOKE] And now we can
perform the Liberam,
which will free us from the
human world once and for all!
There is nothing
you can do to stop us!
[OPHIUCHUS]
Oh, Celestial Spirit King.
I will not fail you!
[GRAY]
What was with the shaking?
Any ideas?
[GAJEEL] Nope, No clue.
[PANTHERLILY]
I'd like to know how we just
ended up here like this.
[GRAY] Hey! I think that's Erza!
You're here?
What is this place?
We're still trying
to figure that one out.
We all just showed up here,
same as you.
Maybe it's because we were all
able to complete our missions.
Well, we did manage
to close the spirits' gates
without a hitch.
I wish I
could be enthusiastic.
But I can't shake the feeling
that I missed seeing a rare
side of my popsicle prince.
Keep your
fantasies to yourself.
Guess this means yours truly
was the first one to
put a spirit in the dirt!
How's that for manly?
So pumped!
Way to go, Elfman!
I actually beat
Erza at something!
This is the happiest
day of my life!
Might not want
to say that too loud.
I wasn't aware
we were racing.
Closing the spirit gates
is a critical matter,
and making it out to
be a game is juvenile.
However,
if you're hell bent on
testing your
mettle against me,
I'd be happy to
put you in your place.
Okay, children.
Let's try to focus
on the task at hand.
[LEVY] So, how
was your battle, Erza?
Sagittarius was
a real challenge.
It was a tough fight and a
rather vigorous workout to boot.
Has there been any sign
of Natsu and his group?
We haven't seen them
or Lucy and Yukino
since we got here.
Huh...Then the only
gates left belong
to the Lion, the Maiden,
and the Balance.
Wherever Arcadios and
Hisui are, I hope they're safe.
And there's still the matter
of the tremendous
shaking from before.
[HAPPY] Natsu vs. Leo!
Look! The stars!
I think they're
constellations.
Okay. Yeah.
[WENDY] That's the Bull...
[WENDY] The Twins...
[WENDY] The Scorpion...
[WENDY] The Archer...
It's hard
to miss a giant Crab.
And if you connect
that one with those,
you get a couple of tasty tuna!
[CARLA] Simple minds
see simple things.
[CARLA] That's definitely
the Water Bearer.
And the one beneath it...
[CARLA]
...is the Goat!
Cool. How many is that?
If you count Aries,
there are nine total.
Wow...
Admiring your handiwork?
[NATSU] Huh?
[LOKE] Those constellations
belong to the Eclipse spirits
who were defeated
by your comrades.
Darkness, we beseech thee.
Envelop our light and swallow us
into your infinite shadow.
And sever the bonds that
shackle us to the heavens.
Hear me, Lord of the Night.
Release us from our
perpetual enslavement.
We long to be free
of our mortal bonds!
Look, pal,
I came here to rumble,
not listen to you ramble!
Liberam!
Give it a rest! It's over!
[LOKE] O, Lord of Darkness.
O, Lord of Stars.
O, Lord of Eternity!
We beg thee
hear our solemn prayers
and grant us liberation.
Release our spirits
into the infinity
of time and space!
How did he cast
the spell all by himself?
[laughing]
I have Ophiucus
to thank for this miracle.
[LOKE] She told me that
I could complete the Liberam
by sending out power
from this globe
and then channeling it
into the constellations.
I suppose that I should thank
you for making them appear.
Is that true?
[CARLA] We worked so hard
to close their gates,
but we only managed
to make everything worse!
I feel like this
always happens, don't you?
See for yourselves, humans!
[LOKE] Our craving for freedom
can be seen even in the
brilliance of the stars!
But after twelve days of it,
you and your friends
will lose your lives!
Are you sure that kind
of sacrifice is worth it?
Like I said before,
there's no way humans could
possibly understand our torment!
Just like there's
no way you can stop me
from finishing
this sacred ritual.
We'll see about that!
[HISUI] What's happening?
Power is being sent
from the celestial globe
to those constellations.
They appear to belong to
the spirits that
have already been sealed.
If that's the case,
does this mean they
restarted the Liberam ritual?
As much as I
would hate to say it,
I believe so.
This isn't good.
Hold on,
that doesn't make sense.
How? Please, explain.
Think about what
they've done so far.
If they could get
the power they need
by sending it to
the constellations,
why would they
bother performing
the Liberam ritual inside the
Astral Spiritus to begin with?
Yes, I see.
Once they obtained
the celestial globe,
they could've returned
to the spirit world.
Without any humans
to hinder their plans,
they would have been enjoying
their freedom by now.
[HISUI]
It just doesn't add up.
Maybe Leo's had an
ulterior motive all along?
[ARCADIOS]
There's also the possibility
another power
is at play here.
One we're not aware of.
But who could it be?
This "other power"?
[OPHIUCHUS]
Oh, Celestial Spirit King.
I will not fail you!
Whatever we're facing,
our primary goal is still
stopping the Liberam ritual.
I agree.
Given the position
of Ras Algethi
near the head star of the
snake charmer constellation,
Natsu and the others
must be in this direction!
[yelling]
That's right.
Rush to your death!
It makes things easy!
Natsu, move!
Fire Dragon...
[LOKE] Pitch-Black...
Their flames
are gonna collide!
Get ready for
one heck of a show!
...Iron Fist!
...Hammer!
Where's your cat?
You'll have a hard time keeping
up without him carrying you.
After you sucker punched him?
I don't think so!
No way I'm putting him
through that again.
Besides, that dirty light
of yours might leave a stain.
This light
is the purest of all,
for it is fueled by
our desire for liberation.
Any stain it might leave
would still be cleaner
than you mortals.
Sure 'bout that?
'Cause from where I'm standin'
it's not lookin' very pure.
[LOKE laughs]
[LOKE] I'll enjoy watching
the darkness take you.
Keep dreamin'!
Don't just stand there!
Grab the globe or something!
Oh, right.
[HAPPY] On it, sir!
[CARLA] Leave it to us!
No, you don't!
Hold it! We've got
our own party to tend to.
By the time I'm done,
that darkness of yours
will be burning bright again.
Here we go!
[growling]
[yelling]
Nobody said this
thing would fight back!
[CARLA] Is it attacking because
it sensed our intentions?
We have to get closer somehow!
Aye, Sir!
Oh, wow!
It took out an entire mountain!
That thing could
make fishing a breeze!
This is not the time
to be thinking with
your stomach, tomcat!
[WENDY] Look out!
[LOKE] You fool.
The light of Regulus
has been mine to command
since long before you were born.
This pitch-black darkness
has only added to my strength!
Your defeat is a certainty!
So come at me with
your feeble light, if you dare!
I thought you'd never ask!
Fire Dragon...
...Iron Fist!
What the--
My flame lost all its power!
It had none
from the start!
My darkness absorbs all light
and transforms it
into nothingness!
Now do you see
how helpless you are?
Your measly flames
could never hope
to pierce my pitch-black armor!
S'that a fact?
Fire Dragon... Talon!
That cheap trick
is getting old real fast.
I can take my turn,
if you like.
Of course, there's no guarantee
you'll be still be alive
to take yours once
the smoke has cleared.
Care to try?
[NATSU] Be my guest!
This is your
last chance to try again.
Just do it!
Pitch-Black... Punishment!
I knew I shouldn't expect
much from human garbage.
[NATSU grunting]
That's a good one!
If I'm nothing but garbage,
why couldn't you
take me out, Mr. Darkness?
Fire Dragon. Iron Fist!
What happened?
Dude. Come on.
After all that bragging,
I was hoping you might
actually be a challenge.
But you're just a pushover.
Learn your place
before I put you in your grave.
Can it, house-cat!
We both know my flames
are stronger than
your darkness will ever be.
[LOKE] Silence!
You might prove
more entertaining
than I initially thought, human.
I'm glad you're fired up.
We're almost there!
Stay strong!
I believe in you!
A little closer...
Just a little more!
We did it!
[screaming]
Oh no! Wendy!
[LOKE] Are you looking at
your helpless little friends
because you want to
join them in their misery?
My goodness!
Wake up, child!
Quit snoozing, tomcat!
Wendy needs our help, pronto!
I'm up, I'm u--
Wendy! We're coming!
[CARLA] Wake up, Wendy!
Yeah! Good catch! Nice!
Release our spirits
into infinite time and space!
Let the flames of darkness
burn away our celestial prison,
my star-bound brethren!
Let the holy black light
of Liberam
guide us to true freedom!
[LOKE] The time has come!
[whistle blows]
If you thought the
other punishments were bad,
try this one.
A gymnastics ring
and a vaulting horse?
What kind of ridiculous
torture is this?
Don't worry,
it'll make sense
once you're spread-eagle.
I preferred you
as a masochist!
[screaming]
What's with that weird light?
Did you finally decide
to dish out some punishment?
That's obviously not my magic!
I see.
Leo must have managed to
restart the Liberam ritual.
[LUCY] What? But how?
The vaulting horse
will just have to wait.
Now that my absolute
freedom is on the line,
I can't afford to play with you.
Virgo, if freedom is something
that's truly important
to you and the others,
I'll do everything
I can to help!
But there might be
some sort of ritual
that'll give you more
than twelve days to live!
Let's search for it together!
I told you before!
That's more than
enough time for us!
Please, just let
me save all of you!
I don't want you to die!
You're starting to have
trouble with your balance.
How long are we
going to do this?
Is it becoming too much
for you to handle?
Huh?
[LIBRA laughs]
[LIBRA] Staying in balance
is exhausting, isn't it?
And it's about
to get even harder.
Where is that
magic coming from?
[LIBRA] Leo has re-commenced
the Liberam ritual!
No!
That light must be
coming from the globe!
How strange.
I never imagined that this
would throw me off my balance.
[NATSU] Fire Dragon...
[LOKE] Pitch-Black...
...Roar!
It would seem
you're no match
for the power
of darkness after all.
Why don't you try using
your own moves, copycat?
Flame Lotus...
Exploding Flame Blade!
Pitch-Black
And there it is!
The crippling weakness
of all humans!
Do you sense it?
Even your flames
are fading to mere cinders!
What a pitiful sight!
You've been snuffed out.
You should give up while
you still have the chance.
Yeah?
Sorry, fleabag,
I'm a stubborn human.
And you've gotta
run out of fuel sometime.
I suppose that's true.
The light has always posed
a challenge to the darkness.
But the light fades, and the
pitch-black void keeps growing!
Soon my power will be as
limitless as the night sky!
Keep dreaming, psycho.
Oh, it's no dream, mortal.
[NATSU screams]
[CARLA] Oh! Wendy!
Are you all right?
Say something!
The celestial globe!
Happy's trying,
but his approach is a little
on the simple side.
[HAPPY yelling]
Eat rock!
[WENDY] Sky Dragon Roar!
Thanks for the save, Wendy!
I'll give you a fish once
I stop seeing six of you!
Hurry, Carla!
Get me back up to the Celestial
Globe as fast as you can!
But that thing
nearly killed you!
Natsu is putting his life
on the line for us.
I should, too.
I have to take the risk!
That doesn't mean
you should be reckless, child.
I'm not a child!
Okay, Wendy.
I want to get
up above that thing!
[CARLA]
You've got it! Here we go!
That's high enough!
What's the plan?
Jump!
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Shattering Light: Sky Drill!
[WENDY yells]
[CARLA, HAPPY] Wendy!
[WENDY] Thank you.
No use.
The only way we're
getting close to the globe
is by beating Loke,
and he's unstoppable!
That's enough!
Fire Dragon... Ro--
Is something the matter?
You're looking
weaker by the second.
Maybe it's because
every blow you dealt
allowed me to siphon
your flame bit by bit.
Now you're completely powerless!
May these black flames
cleanse us of our fates.
Their light
will merge with ours!
And grant us
truly divine radiance!
Such glory!
Our luster will grow!
Brighter and brighter
by the day.
Eternally!
[NATSU]
You just don't listen, do you?
Why do you persist
when it's obvious
that nothing can
hinder our freedom?
You know exactly
why I won't quit.
If you do this, Lucy'll cry.
There's no way
I'm letting that happen!
That's not our problem!
The tears of a human
mean less than nothing to us.
All we care about is liberty!
You pathetic mortals will
be consumed by time and space.
while we illuminate its splendor
long after you've
faded into memory!
Now vanish into my
Pitch-Black Darkness!
Since you've been stealing
my power this whole fight,
I'll just have to take it back.
You can go on and on about
controlling darkness
if that's what does it for you.
I don't give a crap.
[NATSU] Because no matter
what you think,
you're still our friend, Loke,
and Lucy needs you
to snap out of it!
Black Fire Dragon Mode!
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Pitch-Black
Exploding Flame Blade!
[LOKE screaming]
He pulled it off!
Heck yeah, he did!
It shouldn't
surprise us anymore.
This doesn't make sense!
Natsu just closed Loke's gate!
So how is the
Liberam still going?
This won't end well.
[HISUI]
Something is definitely odd.
Wasn't his gate closed?
The fact that Leo's
constellation is back proves it.
I should have known this
wouldn't be done so easily.
[OPHIUCHUS] Omnia... magna...
stella... rex prae.
Why is the snake chick
beltin' out a tune?
Can you tell what she's saying?
"Omelet, mackerel, and
some shellfish tempura to go".
It's still not the time
to think with your stomach!
It's never the
right time with you.
She's saying,
"Omnia magna stella rex prae."
"All for the sake
of the King of stars."
It can't be!
[NATSU] Jeez!
For a giant snake,
Ophiucus has got some moves!
Right, Happy?
[HAPPY] Shh! Not so loud, Natsu!
I'm concentrating!
[NATSU] I gotta say...
I've never seen you
this serious.
[HAPPY]
That's because I'm having
an intense
internal dialogue
about her at this very moment.
[NATSU]
Internal dialogue? What for?
[HAPPY] To put it simply:
I'm wondering whether
I should treat her
like a snake or a fish.
[NATSU]
You have to think about it?
[HAPPY, NATSU] Next Time:
Ophiuchus, the Snake Charmer
[NATSU] So, did you decide yet?
[HAPPY] Hmm...
A snake, because
she doesn't look tasty!