- HEY, GUYS.  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL,"
IT TURNS OUT THAT LYON
USED TO STUDY MAGIC
WITH GRAY WHEN
THEY WERE KIDS.
10 YEARS AGO,
THEIR MASTER, UR,
USED A SPELL CALLED
"ICED SHELL"
TO TURN HERSELF INTO ICE AND
SEAL AWAY THE DEMON DELIORA.
- Lyon: WE BOTH KNOW YOU'RE
THE ONE WHO KILLED UR.
- Gray: ARE WE GONNA DIE,
OR ARE WE GONNA LIVE?
- ( theme music playing )
- YOU WOULDN'T! YOU'RE NOT
BRAVE ENOUGH TO GIVE YOUR LIFE.
- JUST WATCH ME.
- DON'T DO IT!
- NATSU, ERZA,
ALL MY FRIENDS
IN FAIRY TAIL,
THE REST IS UP TO YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE YOU,
BUT MY TIME IS UP.
ICED SHELL!
- SHUT UP!
- ( gasps )
- ( panting )
- NATSU!
- YOU CAN'T JUST BUST IN
AND STEAL THE SCENE
WITH A BUNCH OF FANCY TALK.
GET TO THE BACK
OF THE LINE, PAL.
- BACK OF WHAT LINE?
- I WAS HERE FIRST,
SO IT'S MY FIGHT.
- WHAT?
WHEN I GOT HERE,
THE FIRST WORDS
OUT OF MY MOUTH WERE
"LEAVE HIM TO ME."
- YEAH, AND I SAID "NO WAY, MAN"
LIKE A SECOND AFTER THAT.
- WHY YOU--
- WHAT?  YOU WANT SOME?
- I DON'T CARE
WHO SAID WHAT,
I'VE GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE
WITH HIM, YOU UNDERSTAND?
AND I'M READY TO DIE
IF THAT'S WHAT I GOTTA DO.
- YEAH?
AND HOW'S DYING
GONNA SETTLE IT?
HUH?
'CAUSE IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY TO ME.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT NOW?
- ( shouts, screams )
- EAT THIS!
- DO NOT FALTER.
WE MUST STRIKE DOWN
ALL WHO OPPOSE
THE COLD EMPEROR.
- ( cheering )
- ( chuckles )
- ( disciples chattering )
- WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
- ( gasps )
NO WAY.
WHOA, THE TEMPLE JUST
UN-TILTED ITSELF.
- OW! ( mumbles )
- THIS IS BAD.
NOW THE MOON'S GONNA
SHINE ON DELIORA.
- PARDON THE INTERRUPTION.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
I TAKE IT YOU DID THIS?
- INDEED I DID, SIR.
THE MOON WILL BE OUT SOON,
SO I THOUGHT I'D TAKE
THE LIBERTY OF STRAIGHTENING
THE TEMPLE FOR YOU.
- THAT WEIRDO FIXED IT
ALL BY HIMSELF?
- AND AFTER I WENT TO ALL THAT
TROUBLE TO MESS IT UP, TOO.
HEY, SO WHAT'D YOU DO
TO FIX IT, HUH?
- HUH?
( laughs )
- TELL ME HOW YOU DID IT,
YOU JERK!
- NOW THAT EVERYTHING ELSE
IS IN ORDER,
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD COMMENCE
THE MOON DRIP CEREMONY.
- ( stammers )
HEY!
WOULD YOU QUIT IGNORING ME,
YOU DEMON-HAIRED FREAK?!
- ( laughs )
- GET BACK HERE!
- NATSU!
- I'M GONNA POUND HIM
A MILLION--
NO, A BILLION TIMES.
I'LL LET YOU HANDLE
THAT ICE GUY.
- ( gasps )
- IT'LL LOOK BAD
IF YOU LOSE AGAIN.
- YEAH.
- AND NOT JUST FOR YOU.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
- Both:
BUT FOR ALL OF FAIRY TAIL.
- ( chuckles )
- MY, MY.
WHAT A BOISTEROUS PAIR YOU ARE.
- TELL ME SOMETHING.
A SECOND AGO WHEN I WAS GONNA
FREEZE US BOTH FOR GOOD,
YOU WERE COUNTING ON
NATSU TO STOP ME
BEFORE I COULD FINISH, RIGHT?
- NO.
THE OPPOSITE IN FACT.
I NEVER THOUGHT
HE'D BE FOOLISH ENOUGH
TO COME NEAR
A SPELL LIKE THAT.
- SO YOU WERE JUST GONNA
STAND THERE AND TAKE THE HIT?
- EXACTLY. BECAUSE SOMEONE
WOULD COME TO RESCUE ME.
YOU ON THE OTHER HAND
WOULD BE FINISHED FOR GOOD.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
- CERTAINLY,
IT WOULD BE INCONVENIENT
TO BE SEALED IN ICE,
BUT MY ALLIES
ARE AS DEVOTED TO
MY CAUSE AS I AM.
AND AS LONG AS
WE'RE ON THIS ISLAND,
THEY COULD USE MOON DRIP TO MELT
THE ICE WHENEVER THEY SAW FIT.
- I DIDN'T THINK OF THAT.
GUESS THE ICED SHELL
IS COMPLETELY USELESS HERE.
- EVEN SO,
YOU STILL WANT TO FIGHT?
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED LAST TIME?
- DON'T FOOL YOURSELF.
YOU COULD NEVER--
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- WHAT?
- JUST FORGET ABOUT DELIORA.
- WHAT KIND OF
NONSENSE IS THIS?
YOUR THREATS DON'T WORK,
SO YOU TURN TO BEGGING?
DOES YOUR GUILD
HAVE A DENTIST
THAT REMOVED YOUR FANGS?
OR ARE YOU JUST A COWARD?
- LYON, THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
- WHAT IS IT?
- UR IS STILL ALIVE.
THE ICED SHELL
DOESN'T KILL ITS CASTER.
IT USES THEIR BODY
TO FORM THE BARRIER.
THE ICE KEEPING DELIORA
SEALED AWAY
WHICH YOU'VE BEEN
TRYING TO MELT
IS ACTUALLY MASTER UR.
SHE ISN'T DEAD.
SHE LIVES ON AS THAT ICE.
I'M SORRY THAT I NEVER
TOLD YOU THE TRUTH BACK THEN.
UR MADE ME PROMISE
TO KEEP QUIET.
- Ur: IF HE FOUND OUT
I HAD BEEN TURNED TO ICE,
HE'D PROBABLY WASTE
HIS ENTIRE LIFE
TRYING TO FIND A WAY
TO UNDO THE SPELL.
- OF COURSE.
- IT'S OVER.
THERE'S NO REASON TO GO
THROUGH WITH THIS ANYMORE.
- ( roars )
- ( grunts )
- YOU IDIOT.
I KNOW HOW THE SPELL WORKS.
I CAN ASSURE YOU
SHE'S NOT ALIVE ANYMORE.
THAT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN A CHUNK OF ICE.
- YOU-- YOU KNEW...
KNEW ALL ALONG?
( grunts )
- KNOWING IS ONE THING,
BELIEVING IS ANOTHER.
AND IF YOU TRULY BELIEVE
UR IS ALIVE IN THERE,
YOU'RE AN EVEN GREATER
FOOL THAN I THOUGHT.
- YOU KNEW THE TRUTH
AND YOU STILL DID THIS?!
( breathes heavily )
- AND WHAT OF IT?
- ( grunts )
- OHH.
IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW CAN YOU MOVE
WITH THAT WOUND?
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
I WANTED TO SAVE YOU.
BUT I GIVE UP NOW.
- YOU WANT THE TITLE OF
STAR PUPIL FOR YOURSELF?
WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT I HAVE TO
FIGHT AGAINST DELIORA SOON.
AND I'D RATHER NOT WASTE
MY MAGIC ENERGY ON YOU.
- THEN WE'LL
JUST USE OUR FISTS.
- ( chuckles ) YOU WANT ME TO
FIGHT YOU WITHOUT USING MAGIC?
THAT'S FINE BY ME.
- ( shouts, grunts )
- AIM FOR YOUR
OPPONENT'S WEAK SPOT
AND HIT IT WITH
ALL YOU'VE GOT.
UR TAUGHT US THAT,
REMEMBER?
- YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO SPEAK HER NAME.
AND I WON'T LET YOU!
( groans )
- GET BACK HERE AND ANSWER
MY QUESTION ALREADY,
YOU FREAK SHOW!
- ( laughs )
- COME ON, MAN.
WHY WON'T YOU JUST TELL ME
HOW YOU FIXED THE TEMPLE?!
THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
WHAT A JOKE.
- ( chuckles )
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THAT'S HOW I FIXED THE TEMPLE
AFTER YOU SO RUDELY TITLED IT.
- WHAT KIND OF CRAZY
MAGIC IS THAT?
- IF YOU REALLY MUST KNOW,
I PRACTICE ONE OF
THE LOST MAGICS.
IN OTHER WORDS, BOTH ITS
STRENGTH AND SIDE EFFECTS
ARE SO POWERFUL
IT HAS BEEN ERASED FROM
HISTORY AS WE KNOW IT.
- SERIOUSLY?
- THAT DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC
OF YOURS IS NO DIFFERENT.
- REALLY?
WHERE'D HE GO?
I'M SICK OF CHASING HIM AROUND!
I WANT TO FIGHT!
- ( grunting )
- WHAT A SHAME.
YOUR FISTS ARE
AS WEAK AS YOUR MAGIC.
- ( shouts )
WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW
KIND OF REMINDS ME
OF SOMEONE ELSE
I USED TO
SPAR WITH AS A KID.
- THIS IS THE END!
- AAH!
- ( gasps )
- Natsu: GET UP.
- Young Natsu: GET UP.
- NATSU.
- ( panting )
- COME ON. GET UP.
- YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO NEEDS TO GET UP,
SO YOU COME ON.
- ( both shout )
( both panting )
- SORRY, BUT YOU LOSE.
- HOLD ON.
THIS FIGHT'S NOT NEAR OVER,
GRAY.
- WELL, IF THAT'S
THE WAY YOU WANT IT...
- ( both shout )
- ( panting )
THAT SETTLES IT. YOU WERE
NO MATCH FOR ME AFTER ALL.
- HOLD ON.
THIS FIGHT'S
NOT OVER JUST YET.
- ( sighs ) I SHOULD HAVE KILLED
YOU WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE!
- AAH!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
STEP UP YOUR GAME
IF YOU WANT TO BEAT ME.
- ( shouts )
- I DIDN'T GIVE UP
AGAINST NATSU,
AND I WON'T AGAINST YOU!
( grunts )
I'M NOT GONNA LOSE.
YOU HEAR ME?
- ( both grunting )
- I'M NOT GONNA LOSE!
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
'CAUSE I WANNA WIN!
- Both:
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- ( grunts )
I WON'T LOSE.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- YOU CAN NEVER DEFEAT ME!
- I REMEMBER LOOKING
AT THE SKY THAT DAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT IT WAS SO BLUE
IT MADE ME ANGRY.
( shouts )
- AAH!
- NOTICE ANYTHING STRANGE, LUCY?
- YEAH.  EVEN THOUGH
THERE'S A BUNCH OF THEM,
THEIR MAGIC SEEMS WEAK
FOR SOME REASON.
- EXACTLY.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
THERE ARE ONLY
FIVE WIZARDS AMONG THEM.
- OH, MAN. GUESS THAT MEANS I'M
GONNA HAVE TO GO EASY ON THEM.
- JUST KEEP TELLING
YOURSELF THAT.
- DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
HANDLE THIS ONE?
- OH, YOU BETCHA.
OPEN, GATE OF THE GIANT CRAB.
CANCER!
- CANCER.
- HMM.
WE'VE MET BEFORE, HAVEN'T WE?
- INDEED WE HAVE.
AND AS ALWAYS,
I AM AT YOUR SERVICE, MISS.
- I THOUGHT YOU ALWAYS SAID
BABY? WHAT'S WITH MISS?
AND AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE AT MY SERVICE?!
- I THINK SOMEONE'S
JEALOUS.
- TAKE THEM DOWN!
BUT DON'T KILL THEM.
JUST ROUGH THEM UP, OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT, BABY.
UH, MISS.
- ( panting )
( groans )
THE COLD EMPEROR
DEFEATED IN BATTLE
BY THE LIKES OF YOU?
I WON'T STAND FOR IT.
- THEN GET OVER HERE
AND FIGHT.
- ( groans )
ICE MAKE: SNOW DRAGON!
- ( roars )
- ( shouts )
I THOUGHT WE AGREED
NOT TO USE MAGIC, LYON.
- DON'T BE SUCH
A SORE LOSER.
THIS DUEL WAS
POINTLESS FROM THE START.
DELIORA WILL BE
REVIVED EITHER WAY.
ALAS, IT'S FAR TOO LATE
TO STOP ME NOW.
- I WON'T STOP TRYING.
- TRY ALL YOU WANT,
BUT ZALTI IS PREPARING
TO START THE MOON DRIP
CEREMONY AS WE SPEAK.
- NATSU WON'T LET HIM.
TRUST ME,
THE SECOND YOU
UNDERESTIMATE THAT GUY
IS THE SECOND YOU LOSE.
- ( chuckles )
AT LONG LAST.
- THERE YOU ARE!
I'LL BURN THAT GRIN
OFF YOUR FACE!
- ( laughs )
MUST HAVE TAKEN YOU A WHILE
TO COME UP WITH THAT ONE.
BY THE WAY,
HOW DID YOU MANAGE TO FIND ME?
- I FOLLOWED MY NOSE,
THAT'S ALL.
FOR SOME REASON, YOU TOTALLY
REEK OF LADIES' PERFUME.
- ( laughs ) I WOULD
LOVE TO STAY AND CHAT,
BUT I'VE GOT MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO DO RIGHT NOW.
LIKE REVIVING DELIORA.
- JUST FORGET ABOUT THAT.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN, OKAY?
- REALLY?
AND WHY IS THAT, PRAY TELL?
- 'CAUSE GRAY'S GONNA
KICK THAT ICE GUY'S BUTT.
AND ANY MINUTE NOW,
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR BUTT,
LIKE A BILLION TIMES.
AND THEN THIS
WILL ALL BE OVER.
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
SEE ABOUT THAT.
- HUH?
( gasps )
THAT'S MOONLIGHT.
THERE ARE PEOPLE UP THERE
DOING THE CEREMONY RIGHT NOW?
- ( meows )
- Zalti: ONLY ONE PERSON,
WHICH MEANS THE MOON DRIP ISN'T
TERRIBLY POWERFUL RIGHT NOW.
HOWEVER,
THAT'S HARDLY A CONCERN
SINCE WE'VE ALREADY
GATHERED PLENTY OF MOONLIGHT.
WE JUST NEED TO
GIVE IT A LITTLE NUDGE
TO FINISH THE JOB.
LIKE THIS.
- ( screams )
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD!
DELIORA'S ICE
IS MELTING LIKE CRAZY.
I GOTTA GO STOP THAT GUY
BEFORE THINGS GET UGLY.
- ( chuckles )
- WHOA!
- SORRY,
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
LOOKS LIKE CHASING AFTER ME
WAS A MISTAKE, SALAMANDER.
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME, EH?
- COLD EMPEROR...
- EXCELLENT WORK.
LET'S HEAD TO THE TEMPLE.
- RIGHT.
- NO, WAIT.
- ( gasps )
- WE WON'T LET YOU INTERFERE
WITH THE COLD EMPEROR.
- THOSE HEADPIECES.
YOU PEOPLE ARE FROM
THE CITY OF BRAGO.
AND YOU WANT REVENGE.
- ( screaming )
- ( sighs )
- ( laughs )
- YAH!
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
USING YOUR FIRE MAGIC
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
MIGHT MAKE THE ICE THAT'S
SEALING DELIORA MELT FASTER.
- IF IT COULD BE
MELTED BY FIRE MAGIC,
THEN YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
GONE TO ALL THIS TROUBLE.
BLUFF ALL YOU WANT,
BUT ONCE I'M DONE HERE,
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS STOP THE MOON DRIP
AND IT'S GAME OVER.
- ( laughs )
I MUST SAY,
I TOOK YOU FOR A FOOL,
BUT WHEN PUSH COMES TO SHOVE
IT SEEMS YOU'RE SURPRISINGLY
CLEVER, SALAMANDER.
- I GOT A BAD FEELING
THAT AIN'T NATSU.
- THE CEREMONY IS FINALLY
REACHING COMPLETION.
THE ICE SEALING DELIORA
HAS BEGUN TO MELT AWAY.
- UR...
- THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO.
IT'S TOO LATE
TO STOP ME.
YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
HAVE FAILED.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW LONG I'VE WAITED
FOR THIS MOMENT, GRAY?
SINCE I SAW YOU LAST,
I'VE BEEN GATHERING KNOWLEDGE
AND ALLIES WHO
WILL AID ME.
I WAS FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO DISCOVER THIS PLACE.
AN ISLAND WHERE YOU CAN
COLLECT THE LIGHT OF THE MOON.
GALUNA.
- ( grunts )
- IT WASN'T AN EASY TASK
TRANSPORTING DELIORA
FROM BRAGO.
AND THE MOON DRIP'S
TAKEN THREE YEARS.
- YOU'VE BEEN
WASTING YOUR TIME
ON THIS STUPID PLAN
FOR THREE YEARS?
- STUPID?!
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT!
YOU'VE SPENT THE LAST 10 YEARS
IN SOME FOOLISH GUILD
PIDDLING YOUR LIFE AWAY!
- BECAUSE I PUT MY FAITH
IN WHAT UR TOLD ME.
- ( gasps )
- IN THE WESTERN COUNTRIES,
THERE ARE LOTS OF WIZARDS
WHO ARE MORE POWERFUL THAN ME.
- Gray: SO I WENT WEST
AND EVENTUALLY MADE IT
TO FAIRY TAIL.
AND SHE WAS RIGHT. THE GUILD WAS
SO FULL OF POWERFUL WIZARDS
THAT I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
- I DON'T THINK
I CAN HELP YOU.
THE ICED SHELL IS BASED
ON THE WILL OF ITS CASTER.
AND BECAUSE THAT WILL
IS ABSOLUTE,
A THIRD PARTY
CANNOT MELT THE ICE
NO MATTER WHAT MAGIC THEY USE.
- NO WAY.
YOU'RE TELLING ME
EVEN WITH ALL
THE STRONG WIZARDS YOU GOT,
YOU CAN'T BREAK THE SPELL?
- HMM...
ACTUALLY, NOW THAT
I THINK ABOUT IT,
THERE MAY BE A WAY.
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
THAT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
IF YOU WERE TO
MELT THE ICE,
I'M AFRAID IT WOULD BE
NO DIFFERENT THAN
KILLING YOUR MASTER.
- I DIDN'T KNOW IT
AT THE TIME,
BUT I BET THE OLD MAN WAS
THINKING ABOUT THE MOON DRIP
WHEN HE SAID THAT.
AFTER EVERYTHING
UR DID FOR US,
YOU'D KILL HER WITHOUT
GIVING IT A SECOND THOUGHT.
YOU MAKE ME SICK.
- SAY WHAT YOU WILL.
I DON'T CARE.
MY ENTIRE LIFE HAS
LED UP TO THIS MOMENT.
OUR MASTER IS LONG DEAD.
IF WE WANT TO PROVE
THAT WE HAVE SURPASSED HER,
WHAT CAN WE DO
IN HER ABSENCE?
THINK, GRAY.
THERE'S ONLY ONE ANSWER.
DELIORA.
I WILL SURPASS OUR MASTER
BY DEFEATING
WHAT SHE COULD NOT!
- WELL, I ADMIT THAT'S
A PRETTY AMBITIOUS PLAN,
BUT I CAN'T STOP THINKING
THAT YOU MIGHT HAVE
MISSED THE POINT
SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY.
SOMEONE AS BLIND AS YOU
COULD NEVER BE BETTER THAN UR.
NOT IN A HUNDRED YEARS.
WAKE UP, LYON!
- FOOLED YOU, DIDN'T I?
ICE MAKE: SNOW TIGER!
- ICE MAKE PRISON.
YOU SEE THIS, LYON?
THIS IS WHAT YOU ARE.
- WHAT?
- A BEAST IN A CAGE
LASHING OUT AT A WORLD
HE BARELY KNOWS.
- UTTER NONSENSE.
I'LL MAKE QUICK WORK
OF THAT SPELL OF YOURS.
( gasps )
- SINGLE-HANDED SPELL CASTING
IS TOO UNBALANCED.
YOUR CREATIONS
WILL LET YOU DOWN
WHEN YOU NEED THEM THE MOST.
ICE CANNON!
- AAH!
- UR TAUGHT US THAT,
REMEMBER?
- ( stammers )
GRAY...
- ( sighs )
( groans )
MAN, I SHOULD HAVE SEALED
THIS WOUND UP EARLIER.
- ( roars )
- ( screams )
- MY EARS WEREN'T
READY FOR THIS!
- THAT DOESN'T SOUND
TOO PROMISING.
- IT'S SO LOUD!
- ( whimpers )
- YES, IT'S FREE!
- THAT SOUND...
I COULD NEVER
FORGET THAT SOUND.
- ( Deliora roars )
- DELIORA.
- Gray: THEY DID IT.
THEY ACTUALLY REVIVED IT.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
I CAN DO NOW.
ICED SHELL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: PROFESSOR HAPPY'S
CLASS ABOUT "FAIRY TAIL."
TODAY I'M GONNA TEACH YOU
ALL ABOUT ERZA,
THE ARMORED WIZARD.
SHE'S ALSO KNOWN AS TITANIA,
AND SHE HAS A REPUTATION
AS IMPRESSIVE AS HER WARDROBE.
SHE CAN CHANGE HER WEAPONS AND
HER ARMOR WHENEVER SHE WANTS.
SOME OF HER COSTUMES
ARE KIND OF WEIRD,
LIKE SWIMSUITS AND STUFF.
STILL, SHE'S REALLY STRONG,
EVEN IF SHE'S NOT
TOO GOOD AT LISTENING.
YAY!  THAT'S TODAY'S CLASS.
DISMISSED!  AYE!
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE, NATSU.
YOU ATE THAT FISH
I WAS SAVING, DIDN'T YOU?!
- HUH?  OH, I'M SORRY.
MY BAD.
I'LL CATCH YOU ANOTHER ONE
SOMETIME, OKAY?
- WHAT?!
DON'T EVEN BOTHER.
THIS FRIENDSHIP IS OVER.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WAS GONNA THROW IN
SOME CATNIP TO
SWEETEN THE DEAL,
BUT IF YOU DON'T LIKE ME.
- WELL, I CAN ALWAYS
FORGIVE AND FORGET.
- ARE YOU SURE?  YOU JUST SAID
DON'T EVEN BOTHER, DIDN'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I TOLD YOU CATS HAVE
BAD SHORT-TERM MEMORIES.
- YOU'RE SO FULL OF IT.