Bettin' their lives?
Seriously?
That's crazy;
talk about raisin' the stakes.
Why would they do
something so extreme?
Way to go Yukino.
That's the way a member of the
Sabertooth guild makes a bet!
Kick her butt, Yukino!
You can do it!
It looks like things
are about to get interesting.
I don't think that girl knows
what she's getting herself into.
I'm almost
scared to watch.
She must
be awfully confident
in her skills to make
a wager like that,
but she doesn't stand a
chance against our Kagura.
♪
If you truly intend to
stand behind your wager.
then I suppose I have no
alternative but to accept.
Very well.
Have at you.
[HAPPY] Kagura vs. Yukino!
[BOY SPECTATOR 164A]
They're really gonna do it?
Oh man, so the winner
gets to kill the loser?
That's brutal.
[MALE SPECTATOR 164B]
Are they sure about this?
[CHAPATI] Well,
this is certainly an
unexpected turn of events.
Today's match
is full of surprises.
No way!
This is so unbelievably
not cool!
[KING (MATO)] An exceptional
matchup, if I do say so myself.
This is sure to
be an exciting fight!
[YUKINO]
Facing a member of Sabertooth in
battle is quite
an unfortunate fate.
Is that what
I think it is, Lucy?
Oh wow.
She's a celestial wizard?
[ARCADIOS THINKS]
I had no idea.
Seems there's
another celestial wizard.
[KAGURA] What's that?
A gold key?
I presume it's one
of the Zodiac Keys?
Open.
The Gate of the Two Fish.
What the heck?
Is she summoning
or ordering dinner?
I wonder what this
one's gonna look like.
Me too.
The only Spirit in the
Celestial world who looked
even remotely
fish-like was Aquarius.
If you consider past Spirits,
it should look
something like this.
That's gotta be the creepiest
thing I've ever seen.
Yeah, right.
There's no way that girl's
gonna have such
a powerful Spirit.
I'll bet it looks
more like Gemini.
I'll take tiny sharks over
a giant fish-man, any day.
If it's a big fish,
Happy's gonna die!
I dunno what
that is, but it's not a fish.
How many
times do I have
to tell you to
ignore him, Wendy?
You don't wanna
catch the stupid.
[YUKINO] Come Pisces!
[HAPPY] Wow, they are fishies!
Aw, there's
no need to worry!
Yeah, our girl
is gonna be just fine.
See?
Check it out!
This chick is awesome!
No kiddin', she's
easily dodging their
attacks even though
she's barely movin'.
If I were her, I'd be
scared I was gonna get eaten.
So that's Pisces.
Not too bad.
Yeah, but it's not like
she's that special either.
All she's doin' is running
from 'em and dodgin'.
She's not even
fightin' back!
Look at her keepin'
her cool out there.
Just waitin' for her
chance to finally put
an end to this thing.
[KING (MATO)] This magic
battle has turned out to
be even more exciting
than I expected.
[CHAPATI] Look at that!
Kagura is able to
dodge the Spirit Pisces'
attacks with the
greatest of ease!
[YAJIMA] Impressive.
[JASON] Cool!
[HAPPY] I don't get why she
keeps runnin' from the fishies.
If I were her,
I'd catch 'em and eat 'em!
They're gonna go to waste.
If all you're going
to do is run away
then I suppose I'll have
to stop you in your tracks.
Look!
She's opening another gate?
They're gold and shiny!
You bet they are!
That's because
they're Zodiac keys!
Now open...
The Gate of the Balance.
[YUKINO] Libra!
That is one hot Spirit!
Makes we wanna become
a celestial wizard, too!
She's definitely
a feast for the eyes.
She's so cool!
Now, Libra.
Alter the target's
field of gravity.
[LIBRA] As you wish.
Dang it!
Kagura got trapped!
That Celestial Spirit uses
the same magic as I do!
But with fancy scales!
Si, she's using gravity to
weigh down Kagura's body.
Go, Pisces.
[LIBRA] Impossible!
She escaped
Libra's gravity attack!
But how?
Holy crap!
She's amazing!
Right?
That was one hell of a jump.
Calm down.
Keep watching.
Libra.
Rotate the target's center
of gravity sideways.
[LIBRA] As you wish.
[CHAPATI] That's gotta hurt!
After an impressive escape from
Libra's gravity changing magic,
Kagura finds herself
helplessly pinned down!
[CHAPATI] It looks like
she's in real trouble now!
[JASON] Gravity
is so freakin' cool!
[YUKINO] Attack her!
Boom, now we're talkin'!
That's the power of openin'
two Spirit gates at once!
She's awesome!
We can go ahead and
call it a win for our team.
'Cause here
comes the death blow.
[crowd gasps]
Why did the
fish stop attacking?
Dunno.
Did she run out of magic power?
No, not at all.
Look down there.
[LIBRA] I can't move!
Interesting.
No fair!
She can use gravity magic, too?
Uh-oh.
[LISLIE] Ha.
Kagura taught me
practically everything
I know about gravity
changing magic!
There's a reason that
she's our number one gal!
[MILLIANNA] You said it!
[ARAÑA] She's got this.
[BETH] Show 'em
who's boss!
[LISLIE] This is your chance!
Hurry and finish 'em off!
[KING (MATO)]
What a great match!
This is the real thrill of
the Grand Magic Games!
[CHAPATI] Look at her go!
It's gonna take more than two
Celestial spirits
to faze Kagura!
She's incredible; don't
you think , Mr. Yajima?
She's showing
us a lotta heart.
It's obvious that she has
a strong inner fortitude.
This has gotta
be one of the most
exciting matches I've ever seen!
I mean, seriously, this is
so ridiculously cool, man!
Cool!
[LIBRA] So heavy.
Pisces and Libra,
you may both return now.
[OLGA] Geez, call it a draw!
'Cause This match is gonna
keep draggin' on forever.
Poor Yukino.
Don't worry, you guys!
I just know that our girl
is gonna pull through!
She's gonna win,
ain't she Sting?
Yeah, no doubt.
I'm sure Yukino's
got a lot more
than that in her bag of tricks.
I'm afraid you leave
me with no choice.
I'll have to open
the thirteenth gate.
[LUCY] Hold on,
did I hear that right?
Did she just say
"the thirteenth gate"?
[WENDY] Yeah,
that's what she said,
is there something wrong?
[LUCY] I was always
told that there are
only twelve Zodiac
keys in existence.
I heard about a
thirteenth key but
I thought it was just a rumor.
Apparently that key
belongs to a Celestial Spirit
who's stronger than
all of the Zodiacs.
This gate is one
that's rarely opened.
It is an omen of
very bad luck for you.
[KAGURA]
I don't believe in luck.
[KAGURA] I have never, in my
life, trusted in such a thing.
[KAGURA] Whatever happens
is a result of my choices!
Open.
Gate of the Snake Charmer.
My future
is shaped by my
decisions alone, not by fate!
[YUKINO] Ophiuchus!
[crowd gasps]
Check it out!
What kinda creepy
Spirit is that?
It's huge!
She said "snake charmer"!
But that looks
like an actual snake!
Whatever it is, it's scary.
It does exist. Ophiuchus!
[ARCADIOS THINKS]
A thirteenth Zodiac gate.
This girl is a rare gem, indeed.
[DARTON THINKS]
This doesn't bode well.
Not only are there two celestial
wizards in the tournament.
But both of them happen to
possess powerful Zodiac keys.
[KAGURA] Grudge Sword.
Archenemy.
[KAGURA]
Sheathed Long Sword Technique.
How did she do that?
But she didn't
draw her sword.
Kagura wouldn't unsheathe her
sword just to win
a silly game like this.
[YUKINO] Is this the end?
Your bet was ill-considered.
Sometimes a mermaid
feasts on a tiger.
[CHAPATI] It looks like
that's the match, folks.
[CHAPATI] And the winner is
Mermaid Heel's Kagura Mikazuchi!
I wasn't worried for a second.
Way to go!
Bet they'll never
underestimate her again!
I must admit that celestial
wizard was quite impressive.
She would've done
well against someone else.
This is crazy!
Team Sabertooth hasn't
been able to score a
single point on day two!
I'll bet their master's
not happy about that.
Wow!
That was so freakin' cool!
Aw, yeah!
I'm havin' a
hard time figuring
out what just
happened down there.
Was the Sabertooth girl too
weak or the other too strong?
The latter, I think.
[ERZA THINKS] I had no idea
there was someone like her.
[YUKINO] I've been defeated!
I've let Sabertooth down.
How awful.
Calm down buddy!
[KAGURA] One last thing.
As per our bet,
your life is in my hands.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
I understand completely.
[CHAPATI] Ladies and
gentlemen, that wraps up
day two of the
Grand Magic Games!
[CHAPATI] With a total
of thirty-six points,
the guild currently
in first place is.
Raven Tail!
[CHAPATI] Despite a
total shut-out on day two,
Sabertooth is still hanging
on in second place!
[CHAPATI] But now they share
that spot with Lamia Scale!
Their teams are tied with
a score of twenty points!
[YAJIMA] After scoring
ten points today,
the ladies of Mermaid
Heel jump up two
spots to fourth place with
a total of nineteen points.
[JASON] Blue Pegasus
drops down to
fifth place with
seventeen points!
Cool!
[CHAPATI] And falling
back to sixth place it's.
Quatro Puppy!
No.
You gotta be jokin'!
Hey, man.
Please tell me they're
just foolin' around.
We're not really called
"Quatro Puppy" now, are we?
The two of us made a
man-to-man agreement
in there, so yeah.
[BACCHUS] Alright fellas,
who's drinkin' with me tonight?
Let's get.
[ROCKER] Wild.
[CHAPATI] Although they
both earned an impressive
ten points today, the two teams
who are vying for
last place are...
[CHAPATI] Fairy Tail Team A.
[CHAPATI] And Fairy Tail Team B.
Both with twelve points!
[CHAPATI]
Who knows what exciting
battles await us on day three?
We'll see you then, folks!
[KING (MATO)] That was
a splendid magic game!
[ARCADIOS THINKS]
I can't believe there's
another celestial wizard.
It must be divine luck.
This means the project's
success is practically assured!
[DARTON]
Under the circumstances.
I've no choice but to begin
taking drastic measures.
[JELLAL] Something isn't right.
[JELLAL] It's the end
of day two and yet...
I still haven't detected
the strange magic power
I've sensed in years past.
[LEVY] As day two of the
Grand Magic Games came
to a close only five remained,
until that fateful day.
[ERZA] You haven't
sensed anything?
[JELLAL] No, not yet.
We usually detect a
power reminiscent
of Zeref at the games,
but for some reason,
we've yet to sense it this year.
Why do you think that is?
I'm not sure but I can
think of a number
of possibilities.
[JELLAL] Let's say a wizard
is responsible for the power.
Well, they may not be
attending the games this year.
Or they could
be here in Crocus
but they're not using
that particular magic.
[ERZA] Or perhaps it
could be someone in the
tournament who hasn't had
the chance to compete yet.
[JELLAL] If it's from a
device or a specific location.
Then that makes things
slightly more complicated.
Either the device
hasn't been activated,
or there's some
sort of filter that's
preventing the magic
power from seeping out.
In any case, the fact
that you aren't sensing
it means there's no need
for us to worry right now.
I certainly
hope that's true.
Tomorrow,
I'll do some investigating
of the event organizers.
[ERZA] Try not to draw
any attention to yourself.
[JELLAL] I've learned my lesson.
Ultear drove that point
home loud and clear.
Don't push
yourself too hard.
I won't.
Goodnight, Erza.
[JELLAL] I was
worried we'd never be
able to talk
one-on-one like that again.
[JELLAL] Thank you.
Erza.
It's later than
I thought it was.
Surely the others have
finished their partying by now.
[MILLIANNA] I finally found you!
[ERZA] Who goes there?
[MILLIANNA]
Well aren't you all rosy?
You're...
[MILLIANNA]
Well aren't you all rosy?
It's really you.
It's been a while, Erzy-Werzy!
Millianna!
[MILLIANNA]
I've missed you so much!
[ERZA] It's so good to see you!
Look at you;
have you joined a guild?
Yeah! I'm a member
of Mermaid Heel.
What about Sho and Wally?
Did they join along with you?
Are you kidding me?
We don't allow
any boys in our guild,
so they couldn't
join if they wanted.
Oh, I see.
You'll be happy to know that
they're out traveling the world.
I still talk to them
every once in a while.
That's good.
I can't tell you how
happy I am to see you.
Millianna.
[MILLIANNA]
Likewise, Erzy-Werzy.
[ERZA] Silly me.
I was worried about you.
[MILLIANNA]
Aw, please don't cry!
[ERZA] Sorry, but you are, too!
[Bacchus laughs]
[BACCHUS]
That wasn't half-bad, you guys!
But let's try it one more time;
your soul will always be.
[ALL] Wild!
Now that's the spirit!
You kids really know
how to party, dontcha?
[HAPPY] You're one to talk!
You are the party!
It's gettin' pretty late.
We should probably start
headin' back to our hotel soon.
What in the hell
is keepin' Erza?
[NATSU] Yeah, she's
been gone a long time.
[GRAY] She said she had
to take care of somethin'.
Whatever that means.
Do you think your arms
are gonna be okay tomorrow?
To be honest with ya kid,
I can barely feel
a thing right now!
He's wild, remember?
[BACCHUS] Whoops.
I almost forgot somethin'.
Tell your buddy.
It's Elfman, right?
I hope he makes
a speedy recovery.
Man. That was
a seriously wild battle.
Tell him I hope we
get the chance to lock
horns again at some point
during the tournament.
''Kay, I'll be
sure to tell him for ya.
But don't you forget that I
wanna take you on sometime, too!
Now you're talkin'!
There's a fight I'd love to see!
[BACCHUS] Manly and...
[ALL] Wild!
So noisy.
I wish they'd try
to keep it down.
[NATSU]
Has anybody seen Gramps?
[WENDY] Well, he had a
drinking contest with Bacchus.
He's probably passed
out on the floor somewhere.
[LEVY] Hey, Lu?
Oh, I'm so sorry, Levy
we didn't mean to wake you.
I needed to get up
anyway. Something wrong?
You look upset, are you okay?
That celestial wizard
from the Sabertooth guild.
You mean Yukino, right?
Yeah, she was pretty good.
She had really strong Spirits
and she even had that crazy
thirteenth one,
but she still managed
to lose the match somehow.
What worries me is
she bet her life on that fight.
[LUCY] I can't help but wonder
what's gonna happen to her.
[WENDY] Now that you
mention it, that is distressing.
The only people
you should be
worryin' about
right now is our team.
Whaddya mean, man?
We've still got three
more days to go!
We're just gettin' started!
Yeah, you're right.
All we need to worry about
is doing our best and winning!
[ROCKER] Hey!
You guys got some visitors.
Uh.
Guess you can go in.
Lyon... and ain't
that Sherry's cousin?
It's Shelia.
That is her name, right?
Whatever it is,
I've got a feelin'
she's gonna be
a pain in the butt.
[NARRATOR]
This is the inn where the
Sabertooth guild is staying,
Crocus Gardens.
[JIEMMA]
Your performance today was
utterly pathetic,
you miserable wretches.
[JIEMMA] Don't tell me
you've forgotten why we stand
above the other wizard
guilds in this competition.
[JIEMMA] We don't look
at the insects around us.
We don't talk to them.
We crush them
underneath our feet!
We're focused on something much
greater than this tournament.
[JIEMMA] We aim to stun
the heavens, to rouse
the land beneath us,
and silence the raging seas.
[JIEMMA] For, you see,
that is the Sabertooth way.
[NARRATOR] Master Jiemma rules
his guild with an Iron Fist.
Pity those who disappoint him.
[JIEMMA] Sting!
[STING] Sir?
[JIEMMA] I've decided
to give you one
more chance to redeem yourself.
I don't ever want to see such
a pitiful display
from you again.
Thank you, Master Jiemma.
I'll do my best to live
up to your expectations.
[JIEMMA] Yukino.
[YUKINO] Yes, sir.
There's no excuse for
what happened in your match.
Do you realize
what you have done?
[YUKINO] Yes, sir.
Please forgive me.
I lost to an opponent
from a lesser guild.
I brought shame
to Sabertooth.
I've tarnished our good name.
[JIEMMA] That's not
what I'm talking about!
[JIEMMA] You chose to bet your
life on the battle and you lost.
Even worse, you let your enemy
show mercy on
you and your guild!
[JIEMMA] You are an
embarrassment to Sabertooth!
Yes.
I'm fully prepared to
accept any punishment
that you feel
is appropriate, sir.
[JIEMMA] Good girl.
Then you will throw it all away.
[YUKINO] Yes, sir.
If that is what you wish.
[NARRATOR]
And so, day two of the Grand
Magic Games has come to an end.
[NARRATOR] Though still in
last place, the Fairy Tail guild
has finally hit their stride and
they've managed to
gain some momentum.
[NARRATOR] However,
they remain unaware that
behind the scenes
of the glamorous festival,
something inconceivable
continues to move forward,
little by little.
♪
[HAPPY]
I've got a riddle for ya:
Guess who's about
to pay us a visit?
[NATSU]
That ain't a riddle, dummy!
And why do I have to guess?
Just tell me!
[HAPPY]
No, but I'll give you a hint.
The fifth vowel
and a door-unlocker.
[NATSU]
U. Key?
[HAPPY]
What's the opposite of "yes"?
[NATSU] No!
[HAPPY] Good job!
Now put 'em together
and you've got the answer!
[NATSU] U-key.
No!
[HAPPY] Natsu.
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next time: Hatred at Nightfall!
You mean Yukino, right?
[HAPPY]
You knew the answer all along!
You said it weird on
purpose just to be a jerk!