- Byro:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Happy: WE'RE COMING TO YOU
LIVE FROM THE HEART OF E LAND.
- Natsu: KEEP YOUR EYES GLUED
TO THE TUBE.
- Lucy: THE KING PUT
AN AMUSEMENT PARK IN HIS CASTLE?
WHAT A WEIRDO.
HE MUST BE OFF HIS ROCKER.
- Byro:
DON'T BE FOOLED, YOUNG LADY.
IT'S NOT ALL FUN
AND GAMES IN HERE.
- Natsu: CHECK OUT ALL THE STUFF
I WON'T BE RIDING.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTASY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP
WITH A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: EDOLAS.
IN THIS PARALLEL WORLD,
MAGIC IS A RESOURCE
ON THE VERGE OF VANISHING.
FEARING A LOSS OF POWER, THE
KING FORBADE THE USE OF MAGIC
AND OUTLAWED ALL MAGICAL GUILDS.
DESPITE THIS, A SMALL GROUP
STANDS AGAINST THE TYRANNY
OF THE KING AND WORKS TO HELP
THOSE WHO SUFFER UNDER HIS RULE.
ITS NAME...
THE DARK GUILD, FAIRY TAIL.
MEANWHILE, A GROUP OF WIZARDS
FROM EARTH LAND'S FAIRY TAIL
ARE ABOUT TO FACE OFF
AGAINST THE LEADERS
OF EDOLAS' MAGIC WARFARE UNITS.
THE LIVES OF THEIR FRIENDS
AND THE FATE OF BOTH WORLDS REST
IN THEIR HANDS.
- WILL YOU BE GOOD ANIMALS
AND GO BACK TO YOUR CAGES
WITHOUT A FIGHT?
- DUDE, YOU DON'T GIVE
THE CATTLE A CHOICE.
YOU JUST MAKE 'EM DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- WHAT ARE THEY YAMMERING ABOUT?
- WE ALREADY TOOK THEIR POWER.
SO WE DON'T HAVE TO HANDLE
WITH CARE.
- IF CODE ETD PANS OUT
LIKE THE OLD MAN HOPES,
THAT JUST MEANS THESE EYESORES
BECOME A WASTE OF SPACE.
IF THERE'S ONE THING WE EXCEL
AT, IT'S CLEARING OUT CLUTTER.
HOPE YOU'RE READY
TO MEET YOUR MAKER.
- INCOMING!
- ( laughs )
- ( Happy speaking )
( gasps )
WHERE'D THAT ICE COME FROM?
SO THESE EARTH LAND FREAKS
USE MAGIC LIKE EXCEEDS DO?
- I THOUGHT THEIR ITEM-LESS
MAGIC WAS NOTHING BUT RUMORS.
IT'S TRULY BREATHTAKING
TO BEHOLD.
- THIS CHUMP'S COMBUSTING.
- AND YOU WILL, TOO.
ARE YOU READY TO GIVE
OUR FRIENDS BACK YET?
- SORRY, THAT'S NOT MY CALL.
EVEN IF IT WERE,
IT'D TAKE MORE THAN THAT
TO MAKE ME GIVE UP
ON UNLIMITED POWER.
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO FACE THE
FACT YOUR FRIENDS ARE HISTORY.
IF YOU HAVEN'T LEARNED
HOW RELENTLESS WE CAN BE,
I'LL JUST HAVE TO
KEEP BEATING THE LESSON IN.
- NATSU, LOOK OUT BEHIND YOU.
( shouts )
WHAT ARE WE STANDING IN?
- I'M NOT SURE WE WANNA
KNOW THE ANSWER.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
- I COULD SAY THE SAME TO YOU.
HELL TORNADO.
HELL WHAT?
OH, THAT'S AWESOME.
THAT COASTER'S MAKING
ITS OWN TRACK AS IT GOES.
- YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HAPPY ABOUT IT.  WHATEVER.
FEAST YOUR EYES ON MY COMMAND
BATON, WHICH ALLOWS ME
TO CONTROL EVERYTHING
IN THE AMUSEMENT PARK
FROM THE ROLLER COASTERS
TO THE CREEPY CLOWNS.
- I DON'T CARE IF YOUR WAND CAN
MAKE THE CASTLE DO THE CHA-CHA.
I WRECK THAT COASTER
AND YOU'RE OUT OF PUPPETS.
- MAY WANNA RETHINK THAT
STRATEGY, LAVA BRAINS.
- HOLD UP, WHAT'D YOU CALL ME?
- YOU REALLY THOUGHT I ONLY
HAD ONE?  WHAT A FOOL.
I'VE GOT A WHOLE SYMPHONY
OF HELL COASTERS JUST WAITING
FOR ME TO GUIDE THEM
TO THEIR NEXT VICTIM.
- WHEN I GET OUT OF THIS THING,
YOU'LL BE SORRY.
- WE TAKE SAFETY SERIOUSLY, SO
KEEP YOUR LIMBS AND HEAD INTACT
UNTIL YOUR LIFE COMES
TO A COMPLETE STOP.
SEE WHAT I DID THERE?
- ( wincing )
- THE HELL COASTERS
GO TEN TIMES FASTER
WHEN I BOOST THEIR
MAGIC POWER.
THEIR CRUSHING SPEED DEFEATS
EVEN THE TOUGHEST OPPONENTS
WITHIN FIVE MINUTES.
HUH?
IT HASN'T EVEN BEEN TEN SECONDS.
HOW THE HECK HAVE YOU
SURVIVED THIS LONG
WHEN A JOYRIDE CAN
MAKE YOU HURL?
- WE'RE GETTING DEEPER
BY THE SECOND.
- NATSU ISN'T LOOKING SO HOT.
- WE'VE GOT OUR OWN PROBLEM,
IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED.
- LUCY, YOU GOTTA GET HIM
OUT OF THAT COASTER.
- HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT?
- ( screaming )
- ( laughing )
- ( grunting )
- HEY! YOU'RE KIDDING.  WAIT!
- ( screaming )
- NOW GET UP THERE.
- OH!
NATSU!
GET ME OFF THIS THING.
- WELL, I'LL GIVE HER THIS.
SHE'S BUSTY AND GUTSY.
- NATSU!
- ALL RIGHT, NOW THAT'S DONE.
ICE MAKE GRAPPLING HOOK.
LET'S DO THIS.
- IF YOU COULD PULL OFF
SOMETHING LIKE THAT ON YOUR OWN,
COULDN'T YOU HAVE HELPED FREE
THE DRAGON SLAYER AS WELL?
- THEN THERE WOULDN'T BE ANYBODY
LEFT TO REARRANGE YOUR UGLY MUG.
- ( laughs ) YOU CERTAINLY ARE
CONFIDENT, AREN'T YOU?
- ICE MAKE DEATH SCYTHE.
- SO IT'S ALL ICE?
MOST IMPRESSIVE...
YES, EARTH LAND MAGIC
IS QUITE VERSATILE.
- DID HE WARP MY ATTACK?
- BEHOLD THE POWER
OF MY GLORIOUS MAGIC WEAPON,
THE ROSA ESPADA.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU THROW AT ME,
THIS SWORD'S MAGIC WILL MAKE IT
AS SOFT AS THE FUR
ON AN EXCEED'S BACKSIDE.
- COME ON, NATSU,
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
I CAN'T MOVE THESE ARMS.
- GAH, YOU'RE USELESS.
- SORRY.
- ( laughing )
- ( screaming )
- ( whimpering )
- ( laughing )
- AM I ALIVE?
- HEY, DON'T MISS
THE FINAL TOUCH.
- I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE
ENJOYING YOURSELF.  HUH, WATER?
- SO THEN,
HOW DO YOU LIKE EDOLAS' MAGIC?
I KNOW,
YOU THINK IT'S AWESOME.
IF WE HADN'T TURNED
YOUR FRIENDS INTO A LACRIMA,
ONE DAY IT WOULD ALL VANISH.
DON'T EVEN WANNA THINK
ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW?
- SO THAT'S THE REASON
YOU TOOK THEM AWAY.
YOU'RE GONNA SACRIFICE OUR
FRIENDS AND DESTROY THE EXCEEDS
JUST SO YOU CAN KEEP
YOUR LITTLE TOYS AROUND?
- THAT ABOUT SUMS IT UP.
THEIR DEMISE WILL BRING
OUR SALVATION
THROUGH EVERLASTING MAGIC POWER.
- ENOUGH OF YOUR CRAP.
ALL OF MY FRIENDS
ARE STILL ALIVE IN THERE.
YOU HAD NO RIGHT
TO TAKE THEM.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT LOSING
YOUR MAGIC POWER
SO YOU'RE GONNA DESTROY INNOCENT
PEOPLE TO GET WHAT YOU WANT?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT LIVES HERE.
- NATSU.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
NOW OPEN GATE OF
THE WATER BEARER.
AQUARIUS!
DO YOUR THING.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE YOU
STALLING FOR?
- THE WATER,
I CAN'T CONTROL IT.
- ( laughs )
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN LISTENING?
THERE'S NOTHING
IN THIS AMUSEMENT PARK
I CAN'T USE AS A WEAPON
TO UTTERLY DESTROY YOU.
- LUCY, YOU IDIOT,
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
- Byro: YOUR MAJESTY, I BRING
YOU THE HAPPIEST OF REPORTS.
JUST GIVE THE WORD AND CODE ETD
WILL ENTER ITS FINAL STAGE.
- MEET YOUR END,
YOU FALSE GODS.
- Byro: THE MAGIC
POWER I EXTRACTED
FROM THE DRAGON SLAYERS WAS MORE
THAN WE'D HOPED.
WITH IT, YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO LATCH ONTO AND CONTROL
ANY FLOATING ISLAND
AS YOU SEE FIT.
I DARESAY IT'S RATHER OBVIOUS
WHICH WE SHOULD CHOOSE.
THE ONE WHERE OUR GLORIOUS
LACRIMA IS PERCHED.
JUST IMAGINE IT CRASHING
INTO THAT WRETCHED HIVE
OF FELINE SCUM.  THE COLLISION
WILL VAPORIZE THEM BOTH,
AND THE ESSENCE OF THE EARTH
LANDERS WILL FUSE WITH THAT
OF THE EXCEEDS.
EVERLASTING MAGIC POWER
WILL RAIN DOWN UPON US.
( laughs )
- Narrator: EDOLAS MAGIC,
THE DRAGON CHAIN CANNON.
IT'S A DEVICE FOR FOCUSING
AND RELEASING THE MAGIC POWER
OF DRAGONS.
HOWEVER, IN ITS CURRENT STATE,
IT IS NOT A USABLE WEAPON.
- HERE, MY LORD.
TAKE THE KEY THAT WILL
END THE FALSE GODS.
- YOUR MAJESTY!
PLEASE, WAIT.
DON'T USE IT YET.
- NOW, COCO, HOW MANY TIMES HAVE
I TOLD YOU NOT TO SCAMPER AROUND
LIKE A TODDLER WHEN YOU'RE
IN THE PRESENCE OF OUR KING?
- DON'T ACTIVATE IT.
LILY'S ON THE LACRIMA ISLAND
FIGHTING THE EARTH LAND WIZARDS.
- IMPRESSIVE
FOR A GIANT FURBALL.
- SO THIS IS THE TYPE OF MAGIC
EARTH LANDERS USE.  INTERESTING.
- FIGURES I'D COME TO ANOTHER
WORLD TO FIND A CHALLENGE.
LET'S KICK IT UP A NOTCH AND SEE
WHO CAN DRAW THE FIRST BLOOD.
- I DON'T THINK I'LL BE ABLE
TO CARRY YOU FOR VERY LONG.
- YOU'RE A LOT HEAVIER
THAN NATSU.
THEN AGAIN, I HAVEN'T DROPPED
BIG OLD LUCY YET.
- YOU SURE YOU SHOULD BE SAYING
SOMETHING LIKE THAT OUT LOUD?
WHAT DO YOU THINK SHE'D DO
IF SHE HEARD YA?
- SORRY, LUCY, JUST KIDDING.
- LET ME DOWN.
- YOU SURE?
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT HAVING
SALAMANDER'S CAT
HAUL ME AROUND.  TILL I
CAN FIND MY OWN FLYING CAT,
I'LL SKIP OUT ON THE AERIAL
BRAWLING AND WORK MY MAGIC
ON GOOD OLD DIRT.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- MAGIC POWER
TRANSMISSION COMPLETE.
BUSTERMARM REDEPLOY.
- GOTTA GIVE THE GUY PROPS FOR
CARRYING THAT THING EVERYWHERE.
- NO KIDDING.  IF ONE
PANTHERLILY EQUALS ONE PANTHER
IN LENGTH, THEN THE SWORD'S
EQUAL TO FOUR PANTHERS LONG.
- NO ONE CARES ABOUT THAT.
THEY JUST WANNA SEE A FIGHT.
- YOU MUST BE QUITE CONFIDENT
TO START PLAYING GAMES
IN THE MIDDLE OF A BATTLE.
- HE DID THAT
WITH ONE CLEAN STRIKE.
- SO NOT ONLY IS THE THING
FREAKISHLY HUGE,
BUT THE GUY BEHIND IT KNOWS
WHAT HE'S DOING WITH IT.
- WHEN BUSTERMARM AND I ARE
THROUGH WITH YOU,
YOU'LL BE NOTHING BUT A FADED
STAIN OF RUST
ON HIS GLEAMING CROSS GUARD.
- I'M COOL WITH THAT.
A STAIN OF RUST IS LIKE
A BADGE OF HONOR TO ME.
- YOU WANNA TALK METAL,
GAJEEL'S DEFINITELY YOUR MAN.
- READY?
- COME ON.
- ( shouts )
( laughs )
- IF YOU EXECUTE CODE ETD'S
FINAL STAGE RIGHT NOW,
YOU'LL EXECUTE LILY, TOO.
( gasps )
- WHY SHOULD THAT MATTER TO ME?
- BUT HE'S ONE OF OUR COMRADES.
- COME NOW SACRIFICES FOR THE
GREATER GOOD ARE TO BE EXPECTED
DURING TIMES OF WAR.
- NO FAIR.
I DON'T WANT LILY TO BE A
SACRIFICE 'CAUSE HE'S MY FRIEND.
- WE CANNOT AFFORD TO RISK
OUR KINGDOM FOR THE FATE
OF SOME HAS-BEEN
EXCEED WRETCH.
- WHY ARE YOU BEING SO MEAN?
I WON'T LET YOU DO THIS.
- WAIT!
COME BACK HERE NOW.
- COCO!
- OH!
- YOU'VE LOVED TO RUN SINCE
THE MOMENT YOU COULD STAND,
HAVEN'T YOU, CHILD?
- ( crying )
- AND MUCH LIKE A FATHER,
I'VE ALWAYS ENJOYED WATCHING YOU
SPRINT ABOUT
WITH CAREFREE ENTHUSIASM.
- ( screaming )
- BUT IF YOU DON'T
HAND OVER THAT KEY.
COCO!
BYRO, CAPTURE HER.
DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
- YES, RIGHT AWAY.
- IT HURTS SO MUCH....
RUNNING HAS NEVER
BROUGHT ME PAIN BEFORE.
WHY, YOUR MAJESTY?
I WANT EVERLASTING MAGIC POWER
JUST LIKE YOU DO,
BUT I DON'T WANT LILY TO DIE
JUST SO I CAN HAVE IT.
WHAT DO I DO?
- ( coughs )
NOW WHERE AM I?
AND WHERE'S LUCY?
YOU'RE NOT DEAD, ARE YOU?
YELL IF YOU'RE DEAD....
HEY!
- Lucy: NATSU, IS THAT YOU?
I'M TRAPPED IN THIS THING.
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
- THIS IS NO TIME TO BE PLAYING
IN A BOX, YOU KNOW?
- WHEN I WOKE UP I WAS ALREADY
STUCK IN HERE, SO GET ME OUT.
WHAT'S WITH
THE CREEPY EXPRESSION?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING WEARING
A GENIE OUTFIT?
- HMM? ( screams )
- "THE COMPLETE TRANSFORMATION
ACTOR'S BOX.
COME WITH US AND ENJOY
THE LAND OF FAIRY TALES
WITH SOME FUN AND EXCITING
TRANSFORMATIONS
THAT EVERYONE WILL ENJOY."
- FUN AND EXCITING?
- I THINK THIS DIAL ON THE SIDE
CONTROLS THE COSTUME CHANGES.
- MY REAL CLOTHES BETTER BE
IN THERE.
- OKAY, HERE GOES.
- ( laughing )
- QUIT PLAYING!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( laughs )
- WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT
NOT PLAYING AROUND ANYMORE?
- Hughes: COME OUT, COME OUT,
WHEREVER YOU ARE,
EARTH LAND TRASH.
- LOOKS LIKE HE FOUND US.
- YOU CAN'T SOUND COOL
WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE A PERVERT.
WHY AM I STILL
IN THIS STUPID SWIMSUIT?
NOW CHANGE ME BACK
BEFORE THAT CREEP GETS A PEEP.
HEY, WHAT'S WITH THE STARING?
I JUST FIGURED OUT HOW WE'RE
GONNA BEAT THIS GUY.
- THEY MUST BE WEAKER THAN I
THOUGHT IF I MADE 'EM FLY AWAY.
OR THEY'RE SETTING UP
SOME LAME AMBUSH.
EITHER WAY, I'M NOT WASTING
ANOTHER SECOND LOOKING FOR--
HEY.
WHAT'S UP, STUD MUFFIN?
- ( laughs )
- ( roaring )
- THAT IS SO NOT WHAT
I WAS GOING FOR.
- I THOUGHT THE MONSTERS MIGHT
THINK YOU'RE KIND OF CUTE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I LET YOU TALK ME INTO THIS.
HEY, WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH ALL
THE CHEESY MONSTERS IN UNIFORM?
( screaming )
- THESE ARE THE STUDENTS
OF THE MONSTER ACADEMY.
IN THIS ATTRACTION, YOU GET
A PEEK INTO THE SCHOOL LIFE
OF EVERY DEMON, GOBLIN AND
BLOODSUCKER THAT'S EVER LIVED.
- WHY DOES THIS ALWAYS
HAPPEN TO ME?
THE VERY LEAST YOU COULD DO
IS LET ME CHANGE BACK
INTO MY NORMAL CLOTHES.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- RUNNING FOR MY LIFE,
SO HELP ME!
- NO, NO, THAT'S THE COMPLETE
OPPOSITE OF CUTENESS.
- WELL, EXCUSE ME.
- I THOUGHT THOSE THINGS WENT
FOR THE DAMSEL IN DISTRESS.
- ( laughing )
- GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THIS THE OLD-FASHIONED WAY.
- YOU WANNA THROW DOWN WITH ME
INSIDE MY MONSTER ACADEMY?
IF YOU'RE READY
TO TAKE YOUR FINAL BREATH,
I'D BE HAPPY TO OBLIGE.
- HOW KIND OF YOU.
BUT DON'T GET COCKY.
I'M NOT READY TO CHECK OUT YET.
MUMMY BANDAGE!
- EVERY MONSTER INSIDE THIS
ACADEMY IS A PERFECT SOLDIER
THAT WILL FOLLOW ANY ORDER
I GIVE 'EM.  PRETTY SWEET, HUH?
- YOU'LL HAVE TO
DO BETTER THAN THAT. ( shouts )
- WHAT?
HIS ENTIRE BODY IS ON FIRE.
- THAT'S RIGHT, BUB.
FIRE DRAGON TALON!
FRANKEN KNUCKLE!
- ( grunting )
- HE'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO BEAT FRANK?
COME TO ME NOW,
MONSTER ARMY.
DEFEND YOUR MASTER
WITH YOUR LIVES.
NO!  NO!
- ( laughing )
- LET'S SEE HOW YOU FARE
WHEN THE ENTIRE STUDENT BODY
WANTS YOU IN A COFFIN.
- MY TURN.
- WHY ARE YOU STANDING AROUND?
DESTROY HIM RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?
I'M FREAKING OUT HERE.
- ( growling )
- A REAL MONSTER.
- STUPID MONSTER STUDENTS
LEAVE ME ALONE AND GO BACK
TO YOUR AWKWARD LIFE
OF HOMEWORK AND BOYFRIENDS.
- OW!
- MAN, THAT HURT.
THE MONSTERS VANISHED.
BUT I THINK I KILLED HER.
- ( groaning )
- HUH?  YOUR FEET ARE
IN PRETTY ROUGH SHAPE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- HELP ME, I CAN'T RUN ANYMORE.
- COCO, COME BACK HERE.
- YOU HAVE TO HELP ME, PLEASE.
- HUH?
- TAKE THIS...
WAIT A MINUTE.
SHE'S ONE OF THE EARTH LAND
WIZARDS THAT WE CAPTURED.
THIS IS BAD.
I CAN'T GIVE IT TO HER.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- I SHALL WARN YOU JUST
ONE MORE TIME.
HAND OVER THE KEY
OR YOU'LL REGRET IT.
- MY KEYS?  YOU WANNA STEAL 'EM
AND ENSLAVE MY SPIRITS.
- HUH?
- LIKE I'D LET YOU LAY
A FINGER ON 'EM.
- I DON'T THINK SHE UNDERSTANDS
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- DON'T YOU WORRY, KID.
RELAX.
I WON'T LET HIM HURT US.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: WAIT A SEC.
WHERE'D LUCY RUN OFF TO?
- Happy: LAST I SAW HER, DRACULA
WAS TRYING TO GET IN A NIBBLE.
- IN OTHER WORDS, SHE'S GOOFING
AROUND, RIGHT?  WHATEVER.
COME TO THINK OF IT, GRAY AND
THAT CHIN DUDE ARE GONE, TOO.
- NO WAY!
THE CHEEKY CHIN CHAP?
THE CHEATING CHUMP WHO CHOSE
TO CHIDE OUR CHUM?
- RUN THAT BY ME AGAIN.
CHIN CHUMP IS DOING
WHAT TO OUR CHUM?
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
THERE WAS A "WHOOSH"
AND THE CHIN GUY WENT FLYING.
- HIS CHIN'S GOT WINGS?
- THAT BRINGS UP
A DISTURBING MENTAL IMAGE.