Some hand-to-hand combat, huh?
Sounds like fun to me!
Obey my order.
That won't work.
[SEILAH]
Release my limiter!
She's controlling herself!
[SEILAH growls]
[MIRAJANE gasps]
--[SEILAH roars]
--[MIRAJANE groans]
[MIRAJANE gasping]
[SEILAH, LISANNA scream]
[SEILAH roars]
Careful. Please Mira.
[LUMMY grunting]
[gasps] Oh no.
[LUMMY laughs]
[LISANNA gasps]
What'd I tell ya?
Your sister never had a chance
when she decided to go up
against a legit demon.
Yeah, well, you just haven't
seen what Mira can do yet.
[LUMMY laughs]
Oh, give me a freaking break!
You should've just died
before things got ugly.
And it is gonna get real ugly.
You won't believe the things
Tartaros is capable of.
It's almost game over.
For Fairy Tail, and every other
grody human out there.
[MIRAJANE panting]
Well that hurt. Aw man.
Why'd she hit me, too?
[LISANNA] Has she
lost control of herself?
[MIRAJANE]
She's way too powerful!
I don't think I can beat her
in regular fight like this!
I need to take her over!
It has to work!
I just gotta keep trying!
[SEILAH]
What a fool!
You will never take
control of me!
[SEILAH] I give myself
this simple command!
I must tear my enemy
limb from limb!
[MIRAJANE groaning]
[screaming]
No, Mira!
[SEILAH yells]
[MIRAJANE screaming]
Stop it!
[LISANNA yelps]
[LUMMY]
You gotta watch this next part!
This is where your sister
gets completely wrecked!
I forgot to ask, are there
any hot guys in your guild?
[SEILAH laughs]
[MIRAJANE]
Lisanna. Elfman. I'm sorry.
[CROWD yelling]
[MAN A]
Get out!
[MAN B]
You can't stay here!
[WOMAN A]
Filthy demon!
[WOMAN B]
You don't belong here!
[WOMAN C] You and your
family better leave!
[MAN C] Get outta the village
and take that curse with you!
Oh, no, Mira. Are you okay?
[MIRAJANE]
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
No, none of this is your fault!
I brought this on the moment
I decided to step inside that
church. This awful curse.
[LISANNA, ELFMAN whimper]
[MAN A]
Get outta here, ya demon!
[MAN B]
We're askin' now!
[MAN D]
But we'll make you leave!
[MAN E]
She's possessed by a demon,
it's just a matter of time
before she kills us all!
[ELFMAN]
No, Lisanna! Don't!
[LISANNA whimpers]
My big sister was
the only one here
brave enough to fight
the demon at the church!
She put her own life at
risk to save all of yours!
How can you treat her like
this? The only reason she got
possessed in the first place is
'cause she was tryin' to help!
You should be thanking her!
None of this is her fault!
[LISANNA cries]
It's okay. Don't cry.
[ELFMAN cries]
There's no reason
to cry Elfman.
[MIRAJANE] We're just gonna have
to find a new place to live.
[ELFMAN] It looks
so small from up here.
[LISANNA] We'll find
somewhere better to live.
Let's go.
[MIRAJANE cries]
[LISANNA laughs]
[MAKAROV] Looks nice,
doesn't it? You should go in.
My name's Makarov.
And I'm the master of
the Fairy Tail guild.
[MIRAJANE]
What's that?
This place. Says
so on the sign.
[MIRAJANE]
What a strange name.
[bell tolls]
Looks like a
"Take Over" spell.
You're not really
possessed by a demon.
[MIRAJANE gasps]
I can imagine that
you must have been
frightened to death of that.
But it means that you possess
the power of a demon.
So it's kind of a good thing?
[MIRAJANE]
I still don't want it.
[GUILD MEMBERS chatting]
I've heard about you.
You're Mirajane, right?
My friends say you've
got some cool powers.
Well, what do you think
of our guild so far?
What's wrong?
Don't mind her. She's
just the grumpy type.
Never talks or smiles.
She's like a little dark cloud.
Her brother and sister fit right
in with everyone else, though.
Magic, demons, I don't want
anything to do with this.
It's disgusting...
[MAN A]
Get out!
[WOMAN A]
Filthy demon!
[WOMAN C] You and your
family better leave!
[MIRAJANE] I'm not even human.
Not anymore.
[MIRAJANE]
Everyone's so nice there.
They'll take good care
of Elf and Lisanna.
But I can't stay, I'm sorry.
I'll miss them. I know,
but still. It's for the best.
[ELFMAN]
Hey, Mira!
[LISANNA]
Where are you going?
[MIRAJANE]
Huh?
[LISANNA]
Check this out!
You're not gonna
believe this. But look!
[LISANNA, ELFMAN]
Tah-dah!
I can turn into a cat! See?
I really do have "bear"
hands. Or one at least!
[gasps]
They taught us these spells.
We both wanted to
be more like you.
I can only really make
it work on one arm so far.
Cool, huh?
I know you were feeling
lonely before.
But now the three
of us are just alike.
You're so sweet.
We all have the same magic now!
And it's super awesome!
--Ready, bro?
--Oh, yeah!
[LISANNA]
Uh... I think I messed it up!
I still need a lot
more practice.
Ah! Me, too!
I guess we all have
some work to do
before we try to go on any jobs.
Thank you, Sis.
You protected us with your power
when we needed you the most.
Now we can always
do the same for you.
[LISANNA]
Yeah!
[MIRAJANE]
I was scared at first.
I didn't want this power.
[MIRAJANE grunts]
[MIRAJANE] But I will
do whatever it takes
to protect my family!
And if that means I have to
be a monster or a demon,
then so be it!
Try as you might, you will
never take control over me!
[MIRAJANE grunting]
Mira! You need to get
out of here right now!
Run away!
[MIRAJANE yells]
[MIRAJANE]
If I could just take one part!
What is this? Let go!
[SEILAH]
That weakness I just felt...
[SEILAH] Was her take over
spell working on me?
Impossible, I'm an Etherious!
[SEILAH] I'm done playing
around with her.
It's too dangerous
to let her live!
[SEILAH growls]
Mira, no!
[MIRAJANE] I still believe in
my power, no matter the odds.
I know I can protect
the ones I love.
[SEILAH]
Ah! Demon Eye. Release!
Mira!
This is the good part!
Now die!
[MIRAJANE]
This Macro curse....
Once you've controlled
someone with it,
you can do it anytime you want.
That's what you told me.
[SEILAH] Is this why I felt
that weakness before?
Was she able to take control
of just my curse power?
I gave an order.
Let's see if it works.
[SEILAH]
It's pointless, you fool!
I'm the only one who
can give myself orders!
[MIRAJANE] I never said
that I gave it to you...
Elfman...
[MIRAJANE]
Come here. I need your help.
--[ELFMAN growls]
--[SEILAH screams]
[SEILAH groaning]
He's really here!
[SEILAH gasping]
[LUMMY]
Wasted.
A real man protects his family!
[KYOKA] Lord Mard Geer,
I come bearing bad news.
It seems we underestimated
our enemy.
The Face plan has failed,
and Ezel and Franmalth
have been wiped out.
Add Seilah and Hell's Core
to that list.
Really?
We must summon our master, now.
I'm afraid that we cannot.
[KYOKA gasps]
[MARD GEER] There is a
considerable obstruction
to that goal currently
existing in this world.
I'm talking about magic power.
In order to revive him,
it must be eradicated.
That's what we were
trying to achieve
with our plan to detonate
Face, but it failed.
How I pity you, Kyoka.
[KYOKA]
Mm?
[MARD GEER]
You've never been able
to see the big
picture, have you?
Face was just a speck.
Was what?
[MARD GEER] A miniscule point
in a much larger tapestry.
The range of which a strategist
such as I can see clearly.
In the grand scheme of things,
Face's failure is another
small point among many.
It's nothing worth our worry.
I'm confident in time,
the world's magic power
shall cease to exist.
But how can you be so sure?
Kyoka, tell me what we are.
We are Zeref's demons.
Etherious.
What is our goal?
[KYOKA] Our primary goals
are to revive master E.N.D.
and return to Zeref.
[MARD GEER]
And what are humans?
[KYOKA]
Vile and disgusting creatures.
[KYOKA screams, gasping]
Lord Mard Geer! Why are you...?
[gasping]
[MARD GEER] You brought
humans to our fortress,
and made them your playthings.
[KYOKA]
I tortured them...
To extract information
about Face. [groans]
This fondness you
have for humans.
It will be your undoing.
[KYOKA]
No, that's not true.
[MARD GEER]
This behavior displeases me.
I simply cannot abide
my subordinate
playing with such
lowly creatures.
And thus, you must be
punished for your crime.
Which is not playing
with humans.
But displeasing me, the
Lord of the Underworld.
I understand my lord.
Thank you for the lesson.
Those detestable humans.
[KYOKA screams]
Their ineffective actions do not
concern me in the slightest.
But the thought of them
in my home disgusts me.
Perhaps this calls for Alegria.
[LUCY]
Hold on a sec.
I think Gray is getting into it
with one of the
enemies back there.
I'm pretty sure that I can smell
Mirajane somewhere nearby.
[LUCY gasps]
[WARREN]
Hey guys! Can you hear me?
Warren?
You startled me!
[MINERVA (NEO) yells]
[ERZA] I hear you!
Has something happened?
We've found Mira!
She's safe and sound!
I'm sorry to worry
you. I'm fine now.
[LUCY, NATSU laugh]
[WARREN] Elfman and
Lisanna are with us, too!
That's a relief!
Oh, Warren, hey!
Can you make it so everybody can
hear me through your telepathy?
Yeah, sure. Just
hang on a second.
Okay.
[LUCY]
Wendy and Carla pulled it off!
I don't know how they did
it, but they stopped Face!
[ALL cheering]
[LAKI]
That's great news!
[LUCY] There's something else
we need to tell you about.
Can Master hear me?
I have a message.
Sure Happy. I'll put
you right through.
[HAPPY] We talked to
the soul of Master Hades!
What?!
His soul? That's weird.
What did he tell you?
He said that even though
we stopped Face,
it's not over. He gave
us a message for master.
I don't understand what
it all means, but he told us
that Master has to
"unleash the light".
To do what?
[gasps] He's talking about
The Lumen Histoire!
He can't be serious!
Ah! Please don't
shout like that!
Well, he seemed pretty
dang serious to me.
[WARREN groaning]
[LISANNA]
What's the matter?
[JET]
Uh!
[WARREN groaning]
[JET]
Hey! What's wrong, man?
[ELFMAN] Yeah, what's
happenin' to you?
Come back!
I'm losing the signal!
Warren?!
Please pardon the interruption.
I wish to speak with the
Wizard Guild, Fairy Tail.
[JET] Somebody's hijacking
into Warren's telepathy!
Who the hell are you?!
[MARD GEER]
The Underworld King, Mard Geer.
But knowing who I
am won't save you.
For none of you shall
live to see tomorrow.
Alegria.
[WIZARD A]
Whoa! What's going on?
[WIZARD B] Crap! This thing
is turning upside down!
[WIZARD C]
We're all gonna fall!
[WIZARD D]
Try to hold on to something!
[WIZARD E]
Grab Laxus and the wounded!
What in the hell is this?!
No! It's got me!
It's not... letting go!
[KEYES] The Underworld King's
will is made flesh.
The walls.
[NATSU]
I don't feel so good.
[BOTH grunting]
[LUCY] Help, Natsu!
I'm being pulled in!
[NATSU]
Grab my hand!
[LUCY]
I'm trying!
[BOTH grunting]
[LUCY]
Come on!
[BOTH scream]
[GRAY screams]
[ERZA grunts]
What is all of this?
[MINERVA (NEO)]
Perfect! Now I've got you!
No! Never!
[ELFMAN]
Hold on to me!
[LISANNA]
I am!
[JET]
This stuff is pullin' me down!
[HAPPY]
Someone, help me!
Lord Mard Geer...
The... Alegria.
It will kill our own soldiers!
Consume everything.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[MARD GEER]
Sacrifice.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[ALL groaning]
[GAJEEL, PANTHERLILY grunting]
Stop this! She's mine!
Damn you, Tartaros!
You promised me
that I could kill her!
Lucy!
[MARD GEER]
We are bearing witness
to the endless cycle
of death and rebirth.
Those foolish humans were doomed
once they set foot in here.
This cube is a prison, from
which escape is impossible.
They're forever sealed
inside the Plutogrim!
[KEYES chuckles]
[SILVER] Alegria, the word may
mean happiness to some people,
but to me it's something
different entirely.
It just means that our
paths will never cross.
Magic power?
[gasps]
The Alegria swallowed
up many lives just now.
But one seems to've
avoided its grasp.
[LUCY grunts]
Ow!
[LUCY]
What is all this?
It looks like some
kind of tissue.
The chance of surviving
that curse is less than one
in a billion. What fortune.
Tragic.
One solitary human soul left
to suffer in the underworld.
[LUCY]
So I'm the only one left
after the Underworld
King's curse.
But I'm not gonna
give up on my friends!
No matter how many of these
demons I've gotta fight off!
My celestial spirits and I
will do whatever it takes
to get everyone back
and to save the world from
losing its magic power.
My back is to the wall,
and I might have to
make some hard choices,
but nothing is
gonna stop me!
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
A Strike from the Stars"
The celestial light will
shine though the darkness!