- Narrator: IN A LAND
FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE.
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD
IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST MAGIC IS
MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER INTO
MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS DOT
THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS LEGENDS
HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WOULD NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
- WHY WON'T YOU
GO LOOK FOR HIM?
- I'M NOT LEAVING
WITHOUT MACAO!
- Macao:
I OWE YOU ONE, BUDDY.
- NATSU AND GRAY,
I HAVE AN IMPORTANT FAVOR
THAT I NEED TO
ASK OF YOU.
- Natsu: HEY ERZA,
I'LL COME WITH YOU,
BUT ONLY UNDER ONE CONDITION.
I WANT A REMATCH WHEN WE
GET BACK TO FAIRY TAIL.
- I ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
- Lucy: YOU'RE NOT REALLY
GONNA FIGHT, ARE YOU?
- Doma: THE EISENWALD GUILD
MAY HAVE BEEN DEFEATED,
BUT THAT IS ONLY ONE
SMALL VICTORY
IN A MUCH LARGER BATTLE.
- Michello: THE NUMBER OF
DARK GUILDS HAS BEEN GROWING
AT QUITE AN ALARMING RATE.
- WE HAVE TO COME UP WITH
A PLAN TO ELIMINATE THEM ALL.
- Shitou:
BUT HOW WOULD WE DO THAT?
- HOWEVER IT'S DONE,
WE CANNOT ALLOW ZEREF'S MAGIC
TO FALL INTO
THE WRONG HANDS AGAIN.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW EISENWALD WAS ABLE
TO OBTAIN A TOOL OF FORBIDDEN
MAGIC IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT THE BLAME MAY EXTEND
ALL THE WAY TO
THE HIGHEST LEVELS.
- WHATEVER THE CASE,
ALTHOUGH THEY'RE USUALLY
JUST A THORN IN OUR SIDES,
IT SEEMS FAIRY TAIL PROVED
TO BE QUITE USEFUL.
- THEY TOOK DOWN
AN ENTIRE GUILD
WITH A HANDFUL OF WIZARDS.
THAT IS QUITE A FEAT.
- ( overlapping chatter )
- I STILL DON'T LIKE THEM.
- YOU MAY NOT
WANT TO ACCEPT IT,
BUT THAT'S THE REALITY
OF THE SITUATION.
IN THE END, THE ATTACK ON
THE GUILD MASTERS WAS PREVENTED,
LIVES WERE SPARED
AND NONE OF US HAD TO GIVE UP
OUR HARD EARNED POSITIONS
ON THIS COUNCIL
TO SAVE FACE.
- YOU FOOL!
ARE YOU INSINUATING
THE COUNCIL IS
SOMEHOW TO BLAME?
- ENOUGH OF THIS NONSENSE.
FAIRY TAIL'S GOOD DEEDS
ARE OVERSHADOWED
BY THEIR RECKLESS DESTRUCTION.
- THEN WHY DON'T WE
TAKE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO DISCUSS THE MATTER
WITH THEM?
- ( Happy speaking )
- ( bell ringing )
- Lucy: "EISENWALD'S FAILED
ATTEMPT TO ATTACK
THE GUILD MASTERS WITH LULLABY
ENDED UP BEING BIG NEWS.
IT MADE ALL THE PAPERS,
AND IT SEEMED LIKE
EVERYBODY WAS TALKING ABOUT IT.
BEFORE JOINING FAIRY TAIL,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE IMAGINED
I'D BE PART OF
SUCH A BIG EVENT.
IT FEELS AWESOME, BUT I'M NOT
GONNA LET IT GO TO MY HEAD.
IT STILL MAKES MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT
WHEN I THINK ABOUT
EVERYTHING WE WENT THROUGH.
I HEARD THAT THE AUTHORITIES
CAUGHT MOST OF THE
EISENWALD MEMBERS
WHO WERE INVOLVED.
THEY EVEN GOT A HOLD
OF KAGEYAMA,
SO THAT'S REASSURING AT LEAST.
THE SCARY THING IS,
THEY STILL HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO TRACK DOWN ERIGOR.
I'M WORRIED HE MIGHT SHOW UP AT
FAIRY TAIL LOOKING FOR REVENGE.
BUT I'LL BE OKAY,
'CAUSE I'M WITH THE GUILD'S
STRONGEST TEAM.
ERZA, GRAY, AND NATSU
HAVE MY BACK NO MATTER WHAT.
NOT TO MENTION HAPPY.
FAIRY TAIL IS AWESOME,
AND MY FELLOW MEMBERS
ARE REALLY GREAT PEOPLE.
SO DON'T WORRY, MOM.
I'M DOING FINE.
P.S. PLEASE DON'T TELL DAD
ANY OF THIS, 'KAY?"
( sighs )
MAYBE I'LL DO A LITTLE
SHOPPING LATER TODAY.
SAVING THE WORLD
FROM EVIL IS COOL AND ALL,
BUT SOMETIMES IT'S NICE
JUST TO RELAX AT HOME.
- MAN, 70,000 JEWEL
A MONTH IS DIRT CHEAP
FOR A PLACE LIKE THIS.
YOU TOTALLY SCORED, LUCY.
- INTRUDER ALERT!
( grunts )
NO STRIPPING
IN MY HOUSE, BUDDY.
- HEY, GIVE ME A MINUTE
TO EXPLAIN, WOULD YOU?
I WAS NAKED
WHEN I GOT HERE.
- GET OUT. - SO YOU FORGOT
ABOUT TODAY, HUH?
I FIGURED YOU WOULDN'T REMEMBER,
SO I CAME BY TO REMIND YOU.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- WELL, LET ME TRY
AND JOG YOUR MEMORY.
REMEMBER WHEN NATSU CHALLENGED
ERZA AT THE TRAIN STATION?
- ( crowd cheering )
- FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT!
- SHOW HIM WHO'S BOSS, ERZA!
- COME ON, NATSU!
- Gray: THEY'RE ABOUT
TO FIGHT THEIR REMATCH.
- ( laughing )
- ( gasps )
NO WAY!  THEY'RE REALLY
GOING THROUGH WITH IT?
- OH, HEY, LUCY.
- WELL, IF THOSE TWO
VALUE THEIR MANHOOD,
THEN THEY'D BETTER
GO THROUGH WITH IT.
- ERZA'S NOT A MAN.
- BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT
SHE'S MANLY.
- Lucy: AREN'T YOU WORRIED
THIS FIGHT COULD
TEAR OUR STRONGEST TEAM APART?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OUR STRONGEST TEAM?
- YOU, NATSU, AND ERZA,
YOU DUMMY.
YOU'RE THE THREE STRONGEST
WIZARDS IN THE GUILD.
- WE ARE?  YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT IDIOT
FED YOU THAT LINE?
- ( crying )
- OH, YOU'RE NOT AN IDIOT, MIRA.
- SMOOTH MOVE, GRAY. - I'LL
HAND IT TO NATSU AND GRAY.
THEY'RE TOUGH LITTLE DUDES.
BUT NEITHER OF THEM ARE EVEN
CLOSE TO BEING THE STRONGEST.
THERE ARE GUYS IN FAIRY TAIL
WHO ARE STRONGER THAN
BOTH OF THEM COMBINED.
LIKE THIS GUY.
- BUT CALLING ERZA THE STRONGEST
WOMAN IN THE GUILD
IS A PRETTY SAFE BET.
- AS FAR AS THE GUYS,
IT'S A TOUGH CALL,
BUT I'D PUT MY MONEY
ON LAXUS OR MYSTOGAN.
- ALL I MEANT WAS THE THREE OF
THEM WORK WELL TOGETHER
AND THEY HAVE THE BEST
TEAM CHEMISTRY
IN ALL OF FAIRY TAIL.
- OKAY.  AND THIS IS COMING
FROM THE SAME PERSON
WHO SENT ME ON A MISSION
TO KEEP NATSU AND GRAY
FROM KILLING EACH OTHER
WHEN ERZA WASN'T AROUND?
- GOTTA SAY, I'M PRETTY PSYCHED
TO SEE HOW THIS FIGHT TURNS OUT.
- OH YEAH? I'M SURE SHE'LL END
UP MOPPING THE FLOOR WITH HIM.
- IT'S BEEN QUITE AWHILE SINCE
WE'VE SQUARED OFF LIKE THIS,
HASN'T IT, NATSU?
- I WAS JUST
A LITTLE KID BACK THEN.
TODAY'S GONNA BE DIFFERENT.
'CAUSE I'M TAKING YOU DOWN,
ERZA.
- WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO GO EASY ON YOU.
IN FACT,
I HAVE THE PERFECT ARMOR
FOR THIS OCCASION.
- THAT'S FLAME EMPRESS ARMOR.
GOOD CHOICE AGAINST FIRE MAGIC.
- SO NOW NATSU'S FLAMES
WILL ONLY BE HALF AS EFFECTIVE.
- COME ON, ERZA, AT LEAST GIVE
THE KID A FIGHTING CHANCE.
- HMM.
PUT ME DOWN FOR ERZA
IN THE FIRST ROUND.
- YOU'RE BETTING AGAINST
YOUR OWN BEST FRIEND?
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
PICKING SIDES?
I DON'T WANT
EITHER OF THEM TO LOSE.
- GET INTO THE SPIRIT, LUCY.
- WOW, FLAME EMPRESS ARMOR, HUH?
GOOD NEWS FOR ME.
THAT MEANS I CAN TURN UP
THE HEAT AS HIGH AS I WANT TO.
- ROUND ONE, START!
- ( grunts )
( grunting )
( shouts )
- ( cheering )
( screaming )
- WHOA.
- SEE?  IT'S A GOOD FIGHT, HUH?
- THIS FIGHT SUCKS.
- ( groans )
- THIS FIGHT IS OVER.
- ( crowd chattering )
- MAY I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE?
I HAVE COME HERE ON BEHALF
OF THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
- NO WAY.
- SERIOUSLY?
- WHY WOULD THE COUNCIL
SEND HER HERE?
- AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO NOTICED SHE'S A FROG?!
- AS A RESULT OF
THE EISENWALD INCIDENT,
A MEMBER OF YOUR GUILD
HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH
11 COUNTS OF CRIMINAL
PROPERTY DAMAGE.
ERZA SCARLET,
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST.
- HUH?  YOU'RE PUTTING HER
UNDER A-- WHAT?!
- AND THEN THIS HAPPENED.
- ( murmurs )
- ( sighs )
- Natsu:
THIS ISN'T FAIR, YOU GUYS!
LET ME OUT OF HERE ALREADY!
- NATSU, TRY TO CALM DOWN.
- LET ME OUT!
PRETTY PRETTY PLEASE?
- YOU'LL GO ON A RAMPAGE.
- I'LL BE GOOD, I SWEAR.
NOW PLEASE JUST
TURN ME BACK
TO THE WAY I WAS BEFORE.
- THE SECOND WE TURN YOU BACK,
YOU'LL RUN OUT
TO SAVE ERZA.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
I COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHAT HAPPENS TO HER.
- EVEN IF YOU WANTED
TO HELP HER,
IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN
FACE OFF WITH THE COUNCIL.
- BUT DON'T THOSE JERKS
ON THE COUNCIL REALIZE
THAT ERZA DID
WHAT SHE HAD TO DO
TO SAVE THE LIVES
OF THE GUILD MASTERS
FROM THOSE BAD GUYS
AND THEIR EVIL DEATH FLUTE?!
- IF THE MAGIC COUNCIL
SAYS YOU'RE GUILTY,
THEN YOU'RE GUILTY.
END OF STORY.
THEY DON'T CARE
WHAT WE HAVE TO SAY.
- I JUST DON'T GET IT.
WE'VE DESTROYED PLENTY
STUFF IN THE PAST
AND THEY NEVER MADE
A BIG DEAL OUT OF IT.
- I KNOW.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- IT'S LIKE THERE'S
SOME OTHER REASON FOR THIS.
- Narrator: THIS BUILDING
HOUSES THE FIORE BRANCH
OF THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
AS WE SPEAK, ERZA SCARLET
IS BEING LED DOWN ITS HALLS,
DRAWING CLOSER TO THE TRIAL
THAT AWAITS HER.
- ( croaking )
- ( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
SIEGRAIN.
- ( croaking )
- IT'S BEEN QUITE AWHILE, ERZA.
PLEASE, RELAX.
I'M ONLY HERE IN SPIRIT.
I'M SENDING THIS PROJECTION
FROM ERA.
IN FACT, ALL THE WRINKLED
FACES IN THAT COURTROOM
ARE PROJECTIONS AS WELL.
WE DIDN'T THINK IT
NECESSARY TO BE HERE
FOR SUCH A TRIVIAL MATTER.
- I SEE.
SO YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S BEHIND THIS FARCE?
YOU MAKE ME SICK.
- LET'S BE CIVIL.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A STAUNCH
DEFENDER OF FAIRY TAIL.
BUT THE ELDERS ARE WORRIED THE
BLAME FOR CLOVER'S DESTRUCTION
WILL FALL INTO THEIR LAPS.
AND THE ONLY WAY TO AVOID THAT
IS TO PLACE THE BLAME
ON SOMEONE ELSE ENTIRELY.
YOU'RE THEIR SCAPEGOAT.
- ENOUGH.
- JUST A FRIENDLY WARNING.
IN FACT, IT'S ANOTHER
MATTER ALTOGETHER
I WISH TO DISCUSS WITH YOU.
DON'T LET A WORD SLIP
ABOUT YOU KNOW WHAT.
FOR BOTH OF OUR SAKES.
I MUST JOIN MY
COLLEAGUES ON THE COUNCIL.
I'LL SEE YOU SHORTLY
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
- OH, WOW.  YOU KNOW SOME
VERY IMPORTANT PEOPLE.
- HE'S EVIL.
- ( croaking )
- I'VE WORKED VERY HARD
TO GET THIS FAR, ERZA.
DO NOT STAND IN MY WAY.
- ( gavel bangs )
- THIS COURTROOM
WILL NOW COME TO ORDER.
BEFORE US IS THE DEFENDANT
ERZA SCARLET.
PLEASE TAKE THE STAND,
MISS SCARLET.
- THIS IS WRONG.
WE SHOULD BE THERE
TO TESTIFY.
- BUT LUCY...
- WE'RE NOT GOING TO COURT.
- WHY NOT, MASTER?
WE ALL KNOW SHE'S INNOCENT.
WE CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
AND LET THEM LOCK HER AWAY.
- EVEN IF WE LEFT
THIS VERY SECOND,
THERE'S NO WAY WE'D
MAKE IT THERE IN TIME.
- BUT--
- I'VE BEEN STUCK UNDER
THIS STUPID GLASS
ALL DAY, YOU GUYS.
IT'S GETTING HARD TO BREATHE.
COME ON,
YOU GOTTA LET ME OUT OF HERE!
- Makarov:
YOU SURE YOU WANT OUT?
- HMM.
- ALL: HMM?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IT SEEMS YOU'VE LOST
THE FIRE IN YOUR BELLY.
HA!
- ( grunts )
- IT'S MACAO!
- ( gasps )
- All: THAT WAS YOU?!
- YEAH.  SORRY, GUYS.
BUT I OWED NATSU A FAVOR.
I TURNED MYSELF
INTO A SALAMANDER
SO THAT EVERYBODY
WOULD THINK I WAS HIM.
- LOOK, EVERYONE!
MY DADDY CAUGHT NATSU
TRYING TO SNEAK AWAY.
- HERE'S YOUR CHANCE.
I GOT YOU COVERED.
NOW RUN.
- DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE WENT?
- UH...
- HE WENT AFTER ERZA, DIDN'T HE?
- YEAH, AFRAID SO.
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
THAT IDIOT WILL PROBABLY
TRY TO FIGHT THE WHOLE COUNCIL.
- WOULD EVERYONE
JUST CALM DOWN?
WE'VE NO CHOICE BUT TO
WAIT AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
- ( sighs )
- HMM.
- ERZA SCARLET,
YOU STAND BEFORE THE COUNCIL
TO ANSWER TO CHARGES
STEMMING FROM THE INCIDENT
INVOLVING THE DARK GUILD
EISENWALD.
THESE CHARGES INCLUDE EXTENSIVE
DAMAGE TO OSHIBANA STATION,
THE COLLAPSE OF THE REEYUSIKA
GORGE RAILWAY BRIDGE,
AND THE COMPLETE DESTRUCTION
OF THE CLOVER MEETING HALL.
THERE ARE 11 PROPERTY DAMAGE
CHARGES AGAINST YOU.
ACCORDING TO EYEWITNESS
REPORTS,
THE PERPETRATOR IS DESCRIBED
AS A HEAVILY ARMORED
FEMALE WIZARD.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT IS THIS?
- I'M THE CRAZY LADY IN ARMOR
YOU OLD TIMERS
HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR!
IF YOU'VE GOT A PROBLEM WITH THE
WAY ME AND MY GUILD DO THINGS,
YOU CAN FIGHT ME!
I AM THE ALL POWERFUL ERZA!
YOU THOUGHT I WAS
DESTRUCTIVE BEFORE,
WELL, YOU AIN'T SEEN
NOTHING YET.
( screams )
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THE STUFF I DESTROYED
IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN
THE GUILD MASTERS' LIVES?
WELL?
- ( sighs )
- ( chuckles )
- TAKE THEM AWAY.
- I'M TRULY SORRY FOR THIS,
YOUR HONOR.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, ERZA?
DON'T APOLOGIZE
TO THESE COUNCIL JERKS!
OOPS, I MEAN-- I AM ERZA!
- WORDS CAN'T EXPRESS
HOW ANGRY I AM WITH YOU.
THAT TRIAL WAS JUST
A FORMALITY.
- SERIOUSLY?
- IT'S A GLORIFIED SPECTACLE.
THE COUNCIL IS USING ME AS AN
EXAMPLE TO REMIND EVERYONE
THAT IF YOU BREAK THE LAW,
YOU'LL BE PUNISHED.
IT HELPS THEM MAINTAIN
ORDER IN THE MAGICAL WORLD.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
SO THIS IS ALL FOR SHOW?
- THEY PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
FOUND ME GUILTY
THEN SENT ME HOME WITH
JUST A SLAP ON THE WRIST.
BUT THANKS TO YOU,
I'M STUCK IN A JAIL CELL!
- ( screams )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
- I'M SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY.
YOU MEANT WELL.
- ( grunts )
OW, THAT HURT.
- I SEE.
A FAIRY TAIL WIZARD
CAME TO HER AID.
NATSU DRAGNEEL.
- WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
FRESH AIR COULD SMELL SO SWEET!
I'M GONNA BREATHE IT IN ALL DAY.
IT'S THE SWEET
SMELL OF FREEDOM!
- SHUT UP.
- I'LL NEVER TAKE IT
FOR GRANTED AGAIN.
- PUT A SOCK IN IT, MAN.
- ISN'T HE PRECIOUS
WHEN HE GETS ALL EXCITED?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
STUPID ARREST AND TRIAL
WERE JUST FOR SHOW.
ALL THAT WORRYING FOR NOTHING.
- SO SHE WASN'T
A SACRIFICIAL LAMB,
BUT A SCAPE GOAT.
- YOU MUST BE ONE HECK
OF AN ICE WIZARD,
'CAUSE EVEN YOUR JOKES
LEAVE ME COLD.
HEY, NATSU!
YOU GONNA FINISH
GOING MAN-TO-MAN WITH ERZA?
- UH-OH.
- OH, YEAH, I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY? WANT TO
PICK UP WHERE WE LEFT OFF?
- I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
RIGHT NOW.
- I'M NOT LETTING YOU
OFF THE HOOK THAT EASY!
- I SWEAR.
- ( grunts )
( whimpers )
- ( all gasp )
- HOW'S THAT?
ARE YOU SATISFIED?
- AND HE'S OUT!
- ( laughing )
- WAY TO GO, CHAMP.
- GUESS WE KNOW
WHO THE REAL MAN IS.
- ( giggles )
- ( sighs )
- SIR, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- I'M FINE.  JUST SLEEPY.
HE'S COMING.
- OHH.
- ( thuds )
- NOT AGAIN.
- ( sighs )
- SO TIRED.
- MMM.
- ( sighs )
- ( moans )
- MYSTOGAN.
- I SHALL RETURN.
- NO, WAIT.
LIFT YOUR SLEEPING SPELL
BEFORE YOU LEAVE.
- FIVE,
FOUR,
THREE,
TWO,
ONE.
- ( all gasp )
- ( snores )
- OH, MAN.
WAS MYSTOGAN HERE?
- WHAT A JERK.
- DOES HE HAVE TO
PUT US TO SLEEP
EVERY TIME HE COMES HERE?
- WHO'S THIS MYSTOGAN GUY?
- FOR ONE, HE'S A CONTENDER FOR
FAIRY TAIL'S STRONGEST WIZARD.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
AND FOR SOME REASON
HE DOESN'T WANT ANYONE TO SEE
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE. SO WHENEVER
HE COMES HERE TO TAKE A JOB,
HE CASTS A SLEEPING SPELL.
- THAT'S KIND OF CREEPY.
- MASTER MAKAROV'S
THE ONLY PERSON HERE
WHO'S EVER GOTTEN
A GOOD LOOK AT HIS FACE.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'VE SEEN HIM BEFORE.
( chuckles )
- LAXUS?
- TALK ABOUT RARE.
- YOU'RE NEVER HERE.
- AND HERE'S ANOTHER CONTENDER.
- MYSTOGAN'S JUST
A LITTLE SHY.
YOU SHOULD ALL
RESPECT HIS PRIVACY.
- ALL RIGHT, LAXUS.
YOU AND ME, RIGHT NOW!
- GETTING YOUR BUTT KICKED
ONCE TODAY WASN'T ENOUGH?
- YEAH, PAL. IF YOU CAN'T EVEN
WIN AGAINST THE REDHEAD,
WHY BOTHER WITH ME?
- WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY?
- NO NEED TO GET
ALL WORKED UP, ERZA.
- I'M SAYING THAT IM
THE GUILD'S STRONGEST WIZARD.
- THEN COME DOWN HERE
AND PROVE IT.
- YOU COME TO ME,
LITTLE MAN.
- WITH PLEASURE!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED ON
THE SECOND FLOOR, NATSU.
AT LEAST, NOT YET.
- I THINK YOU MADE HIM GRUMPY.
- SHUT UP!
- THAT'S ENOUGH
OUT OF YOU, LAXUS.
- THE MOST POWERFUL ONE
IN THE GUILD ISN'T A CHICK
OR SOME HOODED WEIRDO.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
THE STRONGEST WIZARD LOOKS LIKE?
YOU'RE LOOKING RIGHT AT HIM.
- HEY, MIRAJANE,
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT WAS THE MASTER
TALKING ABOUT EARLIER?
WHY CAN'T WE GO UP
TO THE SECOND FLOOR?
- THAT AREA'S RESERVED FOR
ADVANCED MEMBERS OF THE GUILD.
THE JOBS THAT ARE LISTED
ON THE REQUEST BOARD UP THERE
MAKE THE ONES LISTED DOWN HERE
LOOK LIKE CHILD'S
PLAY IN COMPARISON.
THEY'RE CALLED
S-CLASS QUESTS.
- S-CLASS?
- THEY'RE JOBS SO DANGEROUS
THAT ONE WRONG MOVE
COULD BE YOUR LAST.
BUT WITH THAT RISK
COMES A HIGHER REWARD.
MASTER MAKAROV HAND PICKS
THE WIZARDS HE THINKS
ARE CAPABLE OF
HANDLING THESE JOBS.
THERE ARE ONLY FIVE PEOPLE
IN THE ENTIRE GUILD
WHO ARE CONSIDERED S-CLASS.
THAT INCLUDES LAXUS,
MYSTOGAN AND ERZA. - HMM.
- I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT
IF I WERE YOU, LUCY.
IN MY OPINION,
THERE'S NO AMOUNT OF MONEY
THAT'S WORTH RISKING
YOUR LIFE OVER.
- YEAH, NO KIDDING.
- HEY, WHERE YOU GOING THERE,
BLONDIE?
- Lucy: WOW.
MYSTOGAN AND LAXUS.
THAT IS SO COOL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MANY
FAMOUS WIZARDS
ARE IN FAIRY TAIL.
AND I THINK I'M STARTING
TO FIGURE OUT HOW
EVERYBODY'S RANKED
WITHIN THE GUILD.
GOTTA START WORKING
MY WAY TO THE TOP.
- WELCOME HOME.
- 'SUP?
- AAH!
YOU GUYS STINK!
WHY DON'T YOU JERKS
WORK OUT AT YOUR OWN HOUSE?
- NOW LUCY, IF WE WANT TO
WORK TOGETHER LIKE A TEAM,
WE GOTTA TRAIN LIKE ONE.
- WE THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE
THE PINK DUMBBELL.
- I DON'T CARE
WHAT COLOR IT IS,
I'M NOT LIFTING
WEIGHTS WITH YOU!
- WE GOTTA KICK IT UP A NOTCH
IF WE WANNA BEAT
LAXUS AND ERZA.
- AYE, SIR.
- I JUST WANT
A LITTLE PIECE AND QUIET.
NOW GET OUT!
- ( whispers ) DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL TRAIN QUIETLY, LUCY.
- WHY DOES THIS KIND OF
STUFF ALWAYS HAPPEN TO ME?
- I'VE MADE A DECISION.
- HMM?
- OUR TEAM IS READY
FOR THE BIG TIME.
S-CLASS.
- YEAH!
CHECK IT OUT!
- HOW DID YOU GET THAT?!
I THOUGHT WE WEREN'T ALLOWED
TO GO ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
- WELL, I JUST
CLIMBED THE STAIRS
AND TOOK IT.
- YOU LITTLE CAT BURGLAR!
- ( giggles )
- SINCE THIS IS OUR FIRST
S-CLASS QUEST,
WE DECIDED TO GO WITH
THE SMALLEST REWARD
WE FOUND ON THE BOARD.
BUT SEVEN MILLION
IS STILL A LOT OF JEWEL.
- WE'RE NOT READY FOR IT.
IF THE MASTER KNEW
WE HAD THIS JOB REQUEST,
HE'D BE FURIOUS.
- YEAH, BUT I THINK HE'LL
END UP BEING PROUD OF US
IF WE ACTUALLY PULL IT OFF.
- ( sighs )
YOU KNOW, THIS MAY BE
THE DUMBEST THING
YOU'VE EVER DONE, NATSU.
IF YOU WANT TO
RISE UP THE RANKS,
YOU SHOULD TRY FOLLOWING
THE GUILD'S RULES.
- JEEZ, WE'RE NEVER
GONNA MAKE S-CLASS
WITH THAT KIND OF ATTITUDE.
- YOU CAN HANDLE THIS
ON YOUR OWN.
I'M STAYING RIGHT HERE.
- BUT THE JOB IS SAVING
A TROPICAL ISLAND.
- REALLY?
- MM-HMM.
- ( steel drums playing )
- Both: IT'S THE CURSED
ISLAND OF GALUNA.
- NO WAY.
DEFINITELY NOT GOING NOW.
- I'LL GIVE YOU HALF
THE FISH I CATCH, LUCY.
- WHAT KINDA INCENTIVE
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
( scoffs )
- FINE.  WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
- AYE. - THAT'S THE BEST IDEA
YOU'VE HAD ALL DAY.
HOLD ON.  FOR CRYING OUT LOUD,
WOULD YOU USE THE DOOR?
( sighs, gasps )
OH, NO!  THEY LEFT
THE JOB REQUEST HERE.
NOW EVERYBODY'S GONNA THINK
I'M THE ONE WHO STOLE IT.
WHAT DO I DO?
IS THIS FOR REAL?
ON TOP OF THE GIANT REWARD,
YOU ALSO GET A GATE KEY?!
HMM.
( giggles )
HEY, WAIT UP, YOU GUYS!
I'VE DECIDED TO COME ALONG!
- Mirajane: MASTER!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENED,
BUT ONE OF THE S-CLASS
QUESTS IS MISSING.
- ( spits )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: WHICH ONE DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD TAKE, NATSU?
- I DON'T KNOW. SINCE THIS
IS OUR FIRST S-CLASS QUEST,
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
PICK THE EASIEST ONE.
- AYE.  THIS GALUNA ISLAND
JOB LOOKS COOL.
AND LUCY WON'T BE ABLE TO
TURN DOWN THE BONUS REWARD.
- OH, THEN GALUNA ISLAND IT IS.
QUICK, GRAB IT BEFORE
SOMEONE SEES US.
- AYE!
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- Natsu: ALL RIGHT. NOW LET'S
HEAD OVER TO LUCY'S HOUSE
AND GET SOME TRAINING IN
BEFORE IT'S TIME TO LEAVE.
- Happy:
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
HER PLACE COULD USE
A LITTLE TESTOSTERONE.