[NATSU] Previously,
on Fairy Tail!
[LUCY] After an intense
battle on Tenrou Island,
our founding master,
Mavis Vermillion,
saved our lives by sealing
us away for a while.
[HAPPY] "A while"?
That's putting it lightly!
When we came back we found
out seven years had passed!
[NATSU] As for what
happened to the Fairy Tail guild
while we were gone, well...
[HAPPY] We're still
tryin' to figure that out.
We know a lot has
changed in seven years.
We're not even Fiore's
strongest guild anymore!
But we've got a chance
to get our top spot back
and we're gonna do it!
[LUCY] In three months,
a major event is being held
to determine which guild
is the strongest in Fiore.
The Grand Magic Games!
From what I've heard,
it's a festival of wizardry
that's filled with all
sorts of magic competitions.
Unfortunately,
while we were stuck
on Tenrou Island
for seven years,
Fairy Tail went from being
Fiore's strongest
guild to the weakest.
We wanna change that
so we're gonna enter
the Grand Magic Games!
The only problem
is the Tenrou Team
has missed out on
seven years of training.
Everyone else has
gotten a lot stronger
and we can't compete
with them as we are now.
We've got three
months until the games begin.
So we've decided to have
a training camp at the beach!
[HAPPY] Song of the Stars!
[CARLA] Listen! We're
not here to play.
We're here
to train!
Let's get to it!
It's hard
to take you seriously
when you're
dressed like that.
There's plenty
of time for training.
but it's important to
balance work and pleasure.
We'll play hard!
Eat hard!
Sleep hard!
Hey wait just a minute,
what about "train hard"?
Yeah, that's
why you're here!
By the time
we're done with you.
Ya might stand
a chance of beatin' us,
'cause there ain't no
way you could right now.
The ocean!
Last one there's
a rotten egg!
Swimming contest!
Sand castle contest!
Eating contest!
Sun tan contest!
[NATSU] That was fun.
I'm ready for a nap.
Look at 'em, they're
kickin' back and relaxin'.
Well, it's only
the first day so
I guess we can
let 'em enjoy it.
My beloved Gray
looks so handsome with a tan!
Okay.
Aw man.
This is gonna be super tough
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the other Fairy Tail members
have started their training for
the Grand Magic Games as well.
However, they've chosen
less tropical locations.
[HAPPY] Whoa,
Natsu's really incredible!
I'm amazed that he can
still do his Fire Dragon Roar
with all the water
pressure down there.
[HAPPY] That was awesome!
[NATSU] You ain't
seen nothin' yet, buddy!
I'm just gettin' started here!
Just watch!
I'm gonna up my
power even more!
Better train or
he'll show me up.
As for me, I always
seem to run out
of magic power
at the worst time,
so I wanna learn
how to sustain it.
To do that,
you must first
strengthen your mind,
thereby enhancing
the vessel
which holds
your magic power.
Feel the land.
The wind.
The air.
Focus on that sensation.
You must
control your breathing
and try to become
one with nature.
There you go.
That's it, Lady Lucy.
Nice work.
Keep going
you need to release
more magic power.
That's tough.
This takes me back
to times I spent
with Lady Layla.
I assisted her with
her training as well.
Say, have you ever
heard of "primordial magic"?
It's the magic from which
all others were created.
The origin.
I remember Hades saying
that he wanted to
get his hands on it.
I guess my
mom must've left out
some stuff when
she told me about it.
She never mentioned Zeref
or the Grand Magic World.
In fact, she didn't bring
up anything scary at all.
What are
you trying to say?
It's hard to explain,
but if the "primordial magic"
my mom told me about
when I was little is real,
then it's not
something that Hades
would ever be able
to get his hands on.
'Cause it's not
something tangible.
[LUCY] From what I
understand, it seems easy to get
but it's actually
very hard to obtain.
[LUCY] And it's
contradictory because
even though it's more
powerful than anything
in this world, it can
also be incredibly weak.
My mother once told me
that all forms of magic
began with the power of love.
So, that's why
I think "primordial magic"
actually refers to "love".
I like the
way you think, Lady Lucy.
If only Hades had been
able to see it that way, too.
Maybe he could've avoided
the depths of darkness.
Gotta get stronger!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
Stronger and stronger!
Aye-aye, Sir!
Anybody who looks down
on our guild is gonna regret it!
'Cause we're still number one!
[HAPPY]
Aye!
I'm gonna show those
good for nothin' jerks
the power of Fairy Tail!
Heck yeah!
You show 'em!
Look! The stars
are so pretty!
[LEVY] Yeah, they are.
Hey, I wonder how training
is going for the others.
Do ya think they
might be out there
looking up at the same
stars that we are right now?
We can do it.
I know we can.
[NARRATOR] It is now day
two of beach training camp
and there are three months
until the Grand Magic Games.
Oh man, I already
feel stronger!
Me too, but
we can't get lazy.
We've gotta
keep training.
I can't believe
that our magic power's
increased so much and
it's only the second day!
Ahh!
Standing close to my darling
while we do the same stretches
has my heart all aflutter!
If we keep
training this hard
for the next three months.
I have no doubt
that we'll be able
to catch up
with everyone else.
All of you other
guilds had better watch out
'cause Fairy Tail
is comin' for ya!
And we're gonna be
Fiore's number one again!
At first I thought,
"We've only got three months?
That's not enough time!"
But now that we've
really started training,
it's more like,
"We've got three months?
This'll be easy!"
Aye!
Princess!
Terrible news!
What the?
Would you please
watch where you pop up?
Do you
want to punish me?
No thanks!
I will if you
ask again.
I'm glad you're
here Virgo
'cause I've been
wondering about something.
What happened to you and
the other Celestial Spirits
when Lucy got stuck in the
Fairy Sphere for seven years?
Did you get
trapped in your world
because she
couldn't summon you?
I'm sorry,
I didn't even think
about how that
might've affected you guys.
I just went ahead
and summoned you during
the Key of the
Starry Heavens incident
like it was no big deal.
Oh, you poor
things, I can't imagine
how dreadfully bored you
must've been because of Lucy!
Don't cry.
I appreciate your concern but
we were never all that bored.
Is there something
wrong, Virgo?
The Celestial
Spirit World
is on the brink
of destruction.
I beg you.
We really need Fairy
Tail's help right now.
That's horrible.
Is there anything
that we can do?
I've been asked to
bring you to our world at once.
The king would like to explain
the situation to you himself.
Alright then,
you lead the way Virgo!
If our friends need
help we won't let 'em down!
Wait a minute.
I thought humans
weren't able
to enter the
Celestial Spirit World.
Well there is one way
in which it's
possible, Princess.
You'll simply have to wear
Celestial Spirit garments.
Here we go.
Hang on! We're
going right now?
Whoa, they just
vanished into thin air!
How come we
don't get to go, too?
This is the Celestial
Spirit World?
Wow! It's so pretty!
And so we meet again,
human girl.
I bid you
welcome to our world.
Massive.
Mustache!
Celestial Spirit King!
So, you're the
ruler of this kingdom?
Does she have
to be so rude?
Indeed, I am.
Is it true
that your world
is on the brink
of destruction?
Smile!
Lucy and friends,
I have requested your presence,
so that we might honor
your remarkable return
from the prison of time.
[KING] Now, let us celebrate!
[LUCY] I thought you
were facing destruction?
[VIRGO] I lied.
[LUCY] What?
[TAURUS] Sorry for tricking
you like that Miss Lucy.
But let me tell ya,
it's worth it to see your face
and udderly
rockin' body right now,
cause that
Celestial World dress
has got my
moo of approval.
[CANCER] We wanted to surprise
you and your friends, baby!
[CANCER] By the way,
if any of you ladies
would like to sport a new
hairstyle for the party,
I'm your man, baby!
[CAPRICORN]
We were extremely happy
when we heard
you had returned
and we wanted to
celebrate with you.
[LYRA] But there's no way
all of us could manifest
in the human world
at the same time
so we decided
to bring you here!
[ARIES] Everyone
wanted to attend the party
and that's the only way
we could make it happen.
Sorry about that!
[SCORPIO] Not many humans get
to come here, but you're wicked!
[AQUARIUS] This is a one-time
thing, so don't get cocky.
[GEMI] Piri piri.
[MINI] Piri piri.
[NATSU] Thanks for
invitin' us over, everybody!
[SAGITTARIUS]
Okily-dokily, let's party!
Are you gentlemen
with me?
[GRAY] Yeah, now that we know
your world's not in danger!
[LOKE] Y'know Lucy,
I wouldn't mind it
if you were to
jump into my arms.
Just sayin'.
[LUCY] Oh, you.
[KING] Let the
merriment begin!
Tonight we shall eat,
drink, and sing with abandon,
as we celebrate the
return of our old friend,
the human girl Lucy,
and her colleagues.
[GRAY] It's been
a while, man.
[LOKE] Shame about
the S-Class trials.
[WENDY] Hello Horologium!
[HOROLOGIUM]
Good to see you, my dear!
[WENDY] I just wanted to say
thanks again for saving my life.
[HOROLOGIUM] You're too kind.
There's no
need to thank me.
[WENDY]
Although I have to say.
It was kinda embarrassing
when my clothes came off.
[HOROLOGIUM] Oh my!
I'm sure it was!
[LUCY]
"My apologies.
Please forgive me,"
he says sincerely.
[AQUARIUS] Excuse me,
but aren't you the girl
who once joined with Lucy?
[JUVIA] What do you
mean by "joined with"?
[AQUARIUS] You got
a boyfriend, dontcha?
[JUVIA] Um, well, no.
[AQUARIUS] Seriously?
A cutie like you?
You'd better step
up your game
or you're gonna
end up like Lucy!
[LUCY] Hey, what's
that supposed to mean?
[LEVY] Wow!
This is incredible!
There are so many books that
I've never even seen before!
[CRUX] Oh Really?
Then please take
one as a souvenir.
[LEVY] Yeah?
[LEVY] He's asleep?
[LUCY] Nah, it just
looks that way.
He's actually thinking.
[HAPPY] Oh hey, Plue!
[CARLA] I always forget that
you're a Celestial Spirit, too.
[HAPPY] Whoa!
There's a ton of 'em!
[GEMI] Nicolas come in
all shapes and sizes!
[MINI] Nicolas come in
[TAURUS] Wow Erza!
I'm over the moon about your
amazingly shapely body!
[ERZA] Really?
[TAURUS] Ya mind jumpin' up and
down a few times, pretty please?
[ERZA] What for?
[LEVY] Ugh, I really
don't like that Spirit.
[WENDY] I kinda don't either.
[NATSU] Yummy!
What is this food I'm eatin'?
[CANCER] That's crab pescatore
with stardust butter, baby!
[ARIES] As well as a
tender and juicy lamb steak
drizzled with Hamal sauce!
[NATSU] I had no idea I
was eating your kind!
[GRAY] This place
is pretty weird
but I think it's
kinda cool too.
[LUCY] Yeah, right?
When I pictured
the Celestial Word
in my head it wasn't
anything like this!
[LUCY] I wonder
which one is my Plue.
[KING] It's only
natural that our world
would surprise you, for it
is a mystery to mankind.
We've had many human
friends over the years
but you are the first
I've invited here.
[GRAY] Wow, that's awesome
but don't you let it go
to your head, okay?
[JUVIA] Hands off!
What do you think you're doing?
♪ I can see you there,
right by my side as always. ♪
♪ You never left or let
me down my friend. ♪
♪ I can feel you there,
close to my heart as always. ♪
♪ Your soul and mine
share a bond made of love. ♪
♪ So as the skies turn grey
and the clouds gather above. ♪
Trying to fight back your tears,
♪ feeling so lost
and alone. ♪
♪ I am the star that
burns for you, ♪
♪ shining through
the night. ♪
♪ Just follow me,
I will guide you home. ♪
♪ And when you're
feeling lost at sea, ♪
♪ listen for my song, ♪
♪ calling you
back to the shore. ♪
[LUCY] That was beautiful.
Thank you.
I love you all!
[KING] Smile!
[ERZA] Wow.
You Spirits certainly
know how to throw a party.
[GRAY] I've never eaten
such tasty food in my life.
[NATSU] I can't believe
that you actually ate the food!
How could you?
[LEVY] Are you sure it's
okay if I take this one?
[WENDY] Hey guys?
Can we keep
these outfits, too?
[HAPPY] This creepy Plue
doesn't wanna let go of me!
[CARLA]
Who'd have thought
that those two would
get along so well?
[AQUARIUS] You've
really got it rough.
Stay Strong!
[JUVIA] No, you have
it much worse than me!
[KING] Take care of
yourself, old friend.
Remember, no
matter where you go,
we will always be with you.
[SCORPIO] Lookin' forward
to workin' with ya again!
[CAPRICORN] Yes, indeed.
Feel free to
call on us anytime.
[LOKE] Tell the guild
I'll visit them soon.
[ARIES] Good bye.
We've enjoyed
having you here
and we appreciate you
looking after Lucy for us.
[LYRA] Bye!
[HOROLOGIUM] Bye!
[KING] This is
goodbye for now.
May the guidance of
the stars keep you well.
Until we meet again!
[ERZA] It's obvious that all
the Celestial Spirits
love you dearly.
[LUCY] Yeah, they're the best
friends a wizard could hope for!
[NATSU] Alright, guys!
We've had our fun;
now it's time
for us to get back
to the beach and train
for the Grand Magic Games!
[GRAY] Right on!
We're in a good place 'cause
we've still got three months
to catch up to
the other guilds!
[HAPPY] Fairy Tail's
gonna take Sabertooth down!
[VIRGO] Oh.
There's something I
probably should've mentioned
before we came here.
[VIRGO] In our world,
time flows a bit differently
than it does in yours.
[NATSU] Wait, are you serious?
I bet it moves slower,
so a year in your world
is the same as a day
back home, huh?
[GRAY] If that's true,
then we should do all
of our training here!
[VIRGO] Not quite.
[VIRGO] It moves faster.
[VIRGO] You see, just one day
in the Celestial Spirit World
is the same as
three whole months
in the human world.
[JET] What took ya so long?
We've been waitin' forever!
[DROY] There's only
five days to go
until the Grand Magic Games!
Hope you guys got lots of
training in while you were gone!
[EVERYONE] It's all over.
Give us our time back,
Mustache Face!
[NATSU] Man, this sucks!
We lost all that time we
were gonna spend trainin'!
[HAPPY] There's
no need to worry!
Apparently, we all have
"Second Origin"
abilities inside us.
If we can draw 'em out
we'll be super strong!
I heard it
kinda hurts though.
[NATSU] I'm willing
to give it a shot!
Wait a second,
where did Erza go?
[HAPPY] Don't
worry about her.
She's busy battling it
out with her own heartache.
[HAPPY] Next time: For All the
Time We Missed Each Other!
for bein' such a baby?
[NATSU] You can
count me out!
And don't come cryin' to me
when she kicks your butt!