[MIDNIGHT] Now, the Infinity
Clock is in our possession.
And very soon, the Amplitude
Limiters will be released.
[JACKPOT] So let's hurry up and
finish the churches! [cackles]
[RACER] More destruction...
the end of everything.
[COBRA] The end is coming.
Just one more
piece to the puzzle, and we
can open up the gates of hell.
[ERIGOR] It's weak. The
gathering storm of carnage
is far too weak.
[MIDNIGHT] Yes... The Infinity
Clock lacks a crucial component.
If great power is
what we truly desire,
there is a great
price to be paid...
We must make the
proper sacrifice.
We can all attest
to that fact.
Go forth! We'll move
the hands of time...
Forcing them onward until
this world is history!
♪
[MACAO] The Oración Seis...
I was hoping I'd never
hear that name again.
I reckon that's why
ol' Makarov was summoned
by the Ten
Wizards Saints?
Mmm...
Our guild was
responsible for
their members' arrests
following the Nirvana incident.
And now it appears that
they've escaped from prison.
While we were asleep
for those seven years,
they got a lot stronger.
We were so utterly
hopeless against them
this last time.
I couldn't do a
single thing to help.
I'm too weak!
Sorry... I'm the one to
blame for all of this.
Please don't be so hard
on yourself, Michelle...
Don't you remember
what Natsu said before?
My dad dumped all
this crazy stuff on us
and expected us to figure it
out without any explanation.
Do you even know how
your father managed to
get himself involved
in all this business
with the Infinity Clock
in the first place?
No clue... unfortunately.
[ERZA] That mystery can
be solved at a later time.
Our highest priority at the
moment is to locate the members
of the Oración Seis...
And from there,
recover the Infinity Clock.
Well, then let's
get movin'!
All we gotta do is start looking
everywhere we can think of,
and we're bound to run into
them eventually, right?
Don't be stupid...
We need to come up with
a solid plan of action
before we do anything.
What?! Who are
you callin' stupid?
All I'm sayin' is if
we wanna find them,
we gotta get out
there and look!
I called you stupid,
flame-for-brains!
Because only a complete
idiot would go running around
with no strategy!
[JUVIA] Oh Gray,
you're amazing!
I love a man who's willing to
fight for what he believes in!
[HAPPY] Get the Infinity Clock!
[WENDY] Everybody is
really on edge today.
[CARLA] Well, how do you
expect them to feel?
We don't know
what to do.
And we're still
missing some key players.
[MAX] Yeah, Gildarts
and Laki haven't come back
from their mission yet.
At times like these...
We need strength from
every single person
in this guild.
[door opens]
[BIXLOW] Yo! What's goin on?!
The Thunder Legion
has returned victorious!
Of course, it really
wasn't such a struggle
for a team as good as ours.
These jobs can be such
an easy payday sometimes,
it's almost criminal.
[FRIED] Excuse me... but
is there a problem here?
[BIXLOW] Okay... So something
called the "Infinity Clock"
is counting down to
the end of the world?
I swear, we leave for a
couple of days and things
go downhill fast.
My, what
unfortunate timing.
Had we still been here, I'm sure
we could've easily dispatched
the Oración Seis
without much of a fuss.
Actually, while we
were on our mission...
[FRIED] I was out
in the marketplace
getting ingredients
for our next meal.
I hope for their sake
you weren't makin'
'em eat more of those
nasty wingfish.
[FRIED] While I was there,
I overheard some soldiers
talking about the destruction
of churches in Sheerotsume.
Two the suspects were
spotted fleeing the scene...
A hooded man carrying a
large scythe and his accomplice
who possessed incredible speed.
I can think of two
bad guys who fit
that description
perfectly.
[NATSU] Erigor and Racer!
[HAPPY] Except now he call
himself the "Grim Reaper".
[FRIED] From what I could
gather, the attacks on churches
have suddenly intensified
in the past several days.
I don't understand why
you never bothered to tell me
or Evergreen about
any of this stuff!
I told you over dinner
that same night.
I can only assume you were
too enraptured by my cooking
to pay very
close attention.
But why target churches?
I still don't see any
clear motive for it.
All I know...
is that ever since
the Oración Seis got their
grubby little hands on
the Infinity Clock, things
have gotten a whole lot worse.
[strained breathing]
[COBRA] I can hear them.
There are four churches
in this area. The priests have
already been taken away.
And the guards don't have a
clue of what's really going on.
It sounds like
it's the perfect time
for more boom-boom-kaboom!
Let's get this party started!
Oh yes! Carnage!
Destruction!
I don't see why we're
still standing around
talking about it
when we'd rather be
having as much fun as yesterday.
What fun? I can't seem
to remember anything
that happened
to us yesterday.
It's not necessary for
you to remember anything.
Just do as we tell you
and nothing more.
I see... I will carry
out the instructions
that I am given.
We've wasted too much
time already. Let's move.
[SOLDIERS yell]
It's the
Oración Seis!
Now men! We must
defend the church!
For these wretched
and miserable souls...
Cost, twenty. Bow and tremble
before an Angel's glory!
[SOLDIERS scream in fear]
[explosion]
[SOLDIER yells]
[panicked breathing]
Concealment magic, huh?
What a pathetic little trick!
[ANGEL] How unsophisticated...
[COBRA] Maybe so, but
our job here is done.
What about the
Anti-Link?
[ANGEL] That's been
done as well... Ah Cobra,
always so cold
and direct.
But those are the two things
I admire most about you.
She's all I cared
about, but she's gone.
Pulled from my hands. And
all I have now... is nothing.
Nothing but delicious
power; that is.
Power from misery.
The sorrow that consumes
my soul is the only thing
still driving me forward.
The pain can only end
when the world itself ends.
There is no other way.
Yes... We must take our
strength from wherever
we can until our ultimate
goal has been reached.
Our failures and regrets...
All those years of pain and
suffering we've endured...
Those are the very
things that define
the Neo-Oración Seis.
[snake hisses]
[gasps] Kinana?
Hold on, now! You're
in no shape to be
walkin' around.
What's wrong? Do
you need some help?
[WAKABA] You better
get back in bed and rest.
That strange
look in her eyes...
[KINANA] We've wasted...
too much time already...
Let's move...
Power from misery. The
sorrow that consumes my soul...
is the only thing
still driving me forward.
[MICHELLE] Kinana, stop!
[KINANA] The pain can only
end... When the world...
itself ends...
My lord. The Legion Platoon
is here as you requested.
I've summoned you
here for but one reason...
To inform you that your power
will be considerably greater
as of today.
You mean, like,
we're gonna be getting
a couple of new members on
the team or something?!
Is that it?
Yes. The archbishop
himself has
requested this addition.
Just one member.
Handpicked from an
extremely select group.
Great Zentopia Prison's
"Forbidden Cell".
What kind of person
are we dealing with here?
[heavy, metallic clanging]
He's... a demon.
What in the heck
is that thing?!
I don't know. But... he's,
like, not even human!
[GUTMAN] Hey there gang!
Ol' Gutman Kubrick
is here and ready to play!
[MARY] He's totally
inside my head!
[BYRO] It's telepathy.
[DAN] And he
sounds so bizarre!
[GUTMAN roars]
[GUTMAN] That doesn't
hurt a big boy like me!
Gutman Kubrick is the
master of Rupture Magic.
His power is known
throughout Fiore.
They call him,
Gutman the Cleaner.
[GUTMAN] Sorry...
That was kinda rude of me.
This thing...
will be joining my
beloved Legion Platoon?
Indeed he is, whether
you like it or not.
[growls]
[footsteps]
[GILDARTS] Yep, this is
one big farm, all right...
Nothing but fields and pastures
as far as the eye can see.
The days of growing
crops are over.
They've withered on the
vine much like those
who once worked this land...
It would be a distant memory,
that is, if there were
anyone left to remember.
Now, this once majestic
estate is nothing more than
a window into the past.
[GILDARTS] So,
long story short...
What you're sayin' is,
it's been a while since
anybody lived here.
This is the place
where Michelle grew up.
The Lobster Family Plantation.
[GILDARTS] On the other hand...
Time has been very kind to
you over the past few years,
if you know what I'm saying.
[LAKI] I know exactly
what you're saying,
and I'm going to tell
Cana you said that.
[GILDARTS] Aw, c'mon!
I was just trying to pay you
a compliment.
[BYRO] So the Oración
Seis were the ones
behind the church attacks.
Are you absolutely sure of this,
your eminence?
[LAPOINTE] I am. And although
their ultimate objective
remains a mystery to
us, it is fair to assume
these blasphemous
acts will continue.
[grumble]
Uhhh... If you don't mind
me asking a small favor.
Dan!
You have a request?
Please share.
If we're able to stop
the Oración Seis,
in return, will you
let Coco out of jail?
I mean, we know going
against church doctrine is,
like, totally a
major big deal.
[MARY] But Coco has been a part
of Zentopia her whole life.
The church
practically raised her!
Seriously, If you
can forgive her,
I know she'd be mega
useful to the archbishop.
We may consider it...
But that decision
hinges on you
completing this mission.
[GUTMAN] Turn that
frown upside down...!
You kids have your best
buddy Gutman with you now!
So don't worry your
silly widdle heads.
Everything's gonna
be just peachy.
Quit talking to us
like children, would ya?
[MALE SOLDIER D]
Your Eminence.
[LAPOINTE] If you'll excuse
me, I'm afraid something
rather urgent has come up.
[LAPOINTE] I apologize
for the wait.
[LAHAR] Cardinal Lapointe.
[LAPOINTE] You're with
the Magic Council's
Custody Enforcement Unit.
What can I help you with today?
This matter concerns
members of the Oración Seis...
Namely those who we had in
custody until recently.
I'm sure word of their
escape has reached you.
There is one small point
of fact I'd like to confirm...
While they were incarcerated, it
seems that a certain individual
from your organization paid
them visits on a somewhat
regular basis.
It's possible he was
connected to the break-out.
[LAPOINTE] I won't stand for
such baseless accusations.
The prison break was
solely the Council's blunder.
Placing blame on our sacred
institution is an outrage.
The very thought of
it is offensive.
You're on
dangerous ground.
Failure to tread
lightly here could lead
to serious repercussions.
[LAHAR] That was unsettling...
His attitude makes it clear
that something
sinister is afoot.
I'm going to need
some help from an old friend.
[MAX] What does all this mean?
[WENDY] Does anybody know
what the writing says?
[CARLA] Her mumblings strike
me as particularly ominous.
Piece to the puzzle...
and then we can open up
the gates of hell.
Do you think maybe
she's finally remembering
something from her past?
Yeah, maybe...
Now that you mention it,
it seems like it was
bothering her a lot lately.
[LUCY] Before she came to
Fairy Tail, Kinana was under
some kind of curse.
[MICHELLE] Poor thing.
Hey... This is
ancient Potamelian!
[WAKABA] This stuff too?
[MACAO] Just like
on the clock hand!
How strange... It appears
to be a description
of a man named Will Neville.
Are you serious?
He's the author of
"Key of the Starry Heavens".
[HAPPY and NATSU] Huh?!
Okay... This is a
pretty rough translation...
But It says, "Will Neville
was once a great wizard
who made contracts with
many Celestial Spirits and
was remarkably skilled
in using them."
Contracts with
Celestial Spirits?
So he was both an author
and a Celestial wizard
to boot... Interesting.
And It goes
on to say... "In life,
Will Neville had
numerous followers.
However, after he fell
into his eternal slumber,
his pupils scattered in all
directions to places unknown."
What's that for?
I think it can help us.
It's a biographical
encyclopedia. Let's see...
Here it is!
[LUCY] "Will Neville...
An author... and a cardinal...
of Zentopia?"
So he was a bird?
A cardinal is a high-ranking
church official.
Uh... According
to this, he was a very
dedicated and prominent
member of the church.
He was also the most
extensive researcher
on Zentopia's history.
That is... until
the day he suddenly left
the church and went missing
for quite a long time.
Does it explain
why he left?
[LUCY] No, it doesn't.
But apparently, several
years after he disappeared,
he re-emerged into the
public eye as Will Neville,
the author of
children's literature.
But there's no
mention of him being
a Celestial wizard in here...
Or that he had any kind
of following.
[MAX] This whole thing
is freaking me out.
I don't understand how
Kinana would know stuff
about him that's not
in the encyclopedia.
And how in the heck does
she know how to write
in that weird
ancient language?
I remember the captain
of the Legion Platoon
said that the Infinity Clock
was the property of Zentopia.
And a prominent former
member of that church
also wrote the "Key of
the Starry Heavens"...
The book your father used
to pass on his message about
how to find the
clock pieces.
[NATSU] I can't
stand it anymore!
What in the heck are we gonna
do about all of this crap?
I say we head out right
now, find this Milk Devil guy
and beat the ever-lovin'
snot outta him!
Will Neville has been
dead for a long time!
Leave the thinkin'
to the grownups!
[JUVIA] Don't back down,
my darling Gray!
If we could somehow figure
out where the Oración Seis
was going to strike next,
we could be waiting there
to ambush them.
Ugh, would ya
keep it down?
I'm trying to get
my beauty sleep.
Dontcha think it's a
little late for that, Cana?
You've practically
been asleep all day!
Yeah, but I just
can't seem to wake up
for some reason,
y'know? Now...
do you boys and girls wanna
find the Oración Seis, or what?
That's right! You
can use your fortunetelling!
Oh, you bet I can!
[MALE SOLDIER E] Don't
give up your ground, men!
[MALE SOLDIER F]
Archers, ready!
Release!
Too slow. Way too
slow. [chuckles]
[gasp]
The storm grows stronger now,
as lightning rips
through the clouds!
[JACKPOT] Slot Magic! I
think we've got another winner
on our hands! Holy cow,
would ya look at that?
Lightning bonus!
Talk about a hot payoff!
It's silent...
There are no more vessels
to be found in this
part of the country.
[ANGEL] Time is running
out very quickly...
And we will do whatever
we can to speed it forward.
[COBRA] I'd be willing
to do more if they would
bring her back to me.
[ANGEL] Now, now Cobra...
You mustn't forget that
our orders come first.
[ROMEO] There we go, all
set! You think that's gonna
work for ya?
It's Perfect! Now I'll
divine where the Oración Seis
will attack next. And,
which of us are gonna go there
and throw them a nice,
little surprise party!
I see it!
So that's all it takes, huh?
Um-hmm.
[CANA] That's it.
If we send these teams
to these locations...
We can stop the attacks
and save some lives.
[NATSU] Cool! So tell
us who's working with who,
and where we're goin'!
[MWithout further ado...
The first is a two-man team...
Composed of Gray and Fried!
How interesting. I've
often wondered if our
magic styles might
complement each other.
I gotta admit, I've
wondered that myself.
Your Enchantments and
my Ice Maker Magic could
be a pretty awesome
combination!
Next up! We've got
Erza and Evergreen!
Let's just hope
that they'll be able
to get along for once.
Yeah, no kidding;
Evergreen's always treated
Erza like they're in
some kinda competition.
Oh... You too, Max.
I'm on their team?!
This is fabulous.
Now we can finally settle
the matter once and for all.
We'll see who is worthy of the
"Queen of the Fairies" title!
The goal of our
mission is to track down
the Oración Seis, but
I'll gladly take you on
anytime after that.
Now, ladies, remember
we have to work together
as a team. Let's try our
best to get along. Okay?
[MACAO] The next team
is Gajeel and Juvia!
Both ex-Phantom Lord
guild members working
on the same team?
Oh no! Why must
I and my darling Gray
be kept apart yet again?!
Why must fate continue to be
so incredibly cruel to us?!
Next up...
Bixlow and... Wendy!
Alright little lady
this is gonna be
a real blast!
I am psyched!
Yeah... I'm looking
forward to working with you.
We'll be a great team!
Sweet! And don't
you forget that my babies
are gonna be on
the team with us!
[TOMMENS] Go team!
Alright! This one's
got Happy, Carla,
and Pantherlily!
Aye! The Exceed Squad
is back together again!
Well, aside from Lily...
I'm not entirely sure
we would fare well against
such a powerful enemy.
And, for the last team!
It's Natsu, Lucy,
Elfman, and Michelle!
So let's go!
We're the only
four-person team?
This is great!
We're together!
I couldn't have picked a
better teammate than you!
And that's all!
Hey! Does this mean
I gotta stay
behind again?!
[ROMEO] Aw, man! I wish
I was goin' with you guys!
[JUVIA] There must be
some way you and I can be
on a team together!
Gajeel, you have to switch
with him right this instant!
No way... My Divination
magic told me this was
the best pairing for the
mission that you've been given.
In that case,
why don't you just let me
switch places with
Fried instead?!
Because that's
the same thing.
I don't think I can
even remember a time
when you and I haven't been
on a team together, Natsu.
Oh crap! What the
heck am I gonna do
if I need to fly around?!
[COCO] Really...? So
you're a survivor from
one of those horrible
church attacks?
[MALE PRIEST A] Yes, and
soon after that happened I
went into hiding for a while.
But then they found me...
and put me in
this prison cell.
I don't understand
why you were imprisoned
after what you've
been through.
[MALE PRIEST A]
I was in their crosshairs for
two reasons. First, because
I am the parish priest...
And second...
I refuse to tell
Cardinal Lapointe what
he wants to know. So he'll
interrogate or silence me.
But what do you
mean by that?
[footsteps]
[LAPOINTE] You filthy traitor.
At last, we finally meet.
[MALE PRIEST A]
Your Eminence!
You'd be wise to tell me
the names of
Will Neville's followers.
[LAPOINTE] This is the fate
that befalls those who dare
defy Zentopia... No...
The fate of those
who dare to defy me.
So pay attention.
[bones cracking]
[MALE PRIEST A screams]
[LUCY] As far as
fortunetelling goes.
Cana is the best there is.
She's almost always dead on!
♪
[HAPPY] You may be the
brawn of the operation,
but I am definitely the brains!
[NATSU] Whoa, back up!
What did you say?!
You don't seriously think
you're the brains, do you?
[HAPPY] Yeah! That is,
like, so obvious!
[NATSU] Sorry but I would
never call you "the brains"!
[HAPPY] Oh yeah?! Well, then
tell me Mister Smarty Pants,
what would you call me?
[NATSU] If I had to answer, I
guess I'd say you're the mascot.
[NATSU and HAPPY] Next time:
Dissonance of Battle!
The mascot, huh? That actually
sounds pretty cool to me!
[NATSU] Didn't expect you
to be so positive about it.
[HAPPY] Come on, we all know I'm
not cut out to be the brains.