- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Lucy:
THE ORACION SEIS IS COMPRISED
OF SIX WICKED POWERFUL WIZARDS,
SO WE'VE TEAMED UP
WITH A FEW POWERHOUSES
FROM OTHER GUILDS
TO TAKE 'EM DOWN A NOTCH.
- Ichiya: MAN...
- Gray:
LYON AND SHERRY ARE HERE?
- Erza: ALONG WITH THAT
LITTLE TROLL, ICHIYA.
- HANDSOME...
MAN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ONE?  IF THAT'S TRUE,
HOW CRAZY INTENSE
IS THIS GUY GONNA BE?
- AAH!
AAH!  AAH!
- HMM?
- UH...
OW.
- HUH?
- ( groans )
- ( gasps )
- I'VE COME FROM
THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD.
MY NAME'S WENDY MARVELL.
IT'S NICE TO MEET
ALL OF YOU.
- Gray and Lyon:
A GIRL?
- Lucy and Sherry:
SHE'S A KID?
- SHE'S NOT HANDSOME.
- NOR IS SHE A MAN.
WHY SHOULD IT MATTER?
- WENDY.
- MARVELL-OUS.
- CUTE.
- NOW THEN, SINCE ALL GUILDS
ARE PRESENT, WE CAN BEGIN.
- HE'S NOT EVEN FAZED BY THIS?!
- Lyon: OBVIOUSLY NOT.
- Sherry: WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS CAIT SHELTER THINKING,
SENDING A LITTLE GIRL
ON THIS KIND OF MISSION?
THEY MUST REALLY
BE HURTING FOR MEMBERS
IF THEY SENT HER
HERE ON HER OWN.
- SHE ISN'T ALONE.
YOU SHOULDN'T JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS, GAUDY TROLLOP.
- ( all gasp )
- OH!
- HMM!
- ( Happy speaking )
- WHAT IS THIS?
- A CAT.
- WHOA, SHE'S JUST LIKE HAPPY.
- SHE CAN TALK TOO?
- WHAT A STUPID CAT.
I'M NOT GAUDY.
- THAT'S YOUR BEEF?!
- OH, CARLA.
YOU FOLLOWED ME HERE?
- OF COURSE I DID.
YOU'RE FAR TOO YOUNG
TO BE TRAVELLING
UNACCOMPANIED, CHILD.
- All: PRETTY KITTY.
- YOU FLIRT WITH CATS TOO?!
- HMM?
- OH...
AAH!
THUMPITY-THUMP,
THUMPITY-THUMP!
( shouts )
( murmurs )
- HMM?
- LUCY, I'LL GIVE YOU MY FISH,
IF YOU TELL THAT VISION
I HAVEN'T BEEN NEUTERED YET.
- KEEP LOOKING UP
MY SKIRT, AND YOU WILL BE.
IT'S ABOUT TIME
THE LITTLE GUY GETS
A TASTE OF HIS OWN MEDICINE.
- ( murmurs excitedly )
- YOU LOVE HER!
- THAT'S MY SCHTICK, COPYCAT!
AND I DON'T LOOK NEARLY AS
CREEPY AS YOU DO WHEN I DO IT!
- SORRY.
I'M PROBABLY NOT
WHAT YOU EXPECTED.
I KNOW I'M MUCH SMALLER
AND YOUNGER THAN MOST OF YOU,
AND I MAY NOT BE
MUCH OF A FIGHTER,
BUT I CAN USE ALL KINDS
OF SUPPORT MAGIC.
SO, PLEASE,
LET ME JOIN THE GROUP.
I'D BE SO EMBARRASSED
IF YOU SENT ME HOME.
- UH--
- All: UH...
- YOU'LL NEVER GAIN
THEIR RESPECT,
IF YOU CAN'T SHOW
CONFIDENCE, CHILD.
- I'M SORRY, CARLA.
- I SWEAR, YOU'LL DRIVE ME
TO CATNIP.
- I CAN'T HELP IT.
- ( sighs )
- FORGIVE ME.
I WAS CAUGHT OFF-GUARD.
BUT REST ASSURED,
NO OFFENSE WAS MEANT.
WE'RE GLAD TO
HAVE YOU ABOARD, WENDY.
- ( exhales )
OH, WOW, YOU'RE ERZA, RIGHT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S REALLY YOU.
- YOU'RE NOT QUITE
THE MONSTER I PICTURED.
- SURELY YOU'VE HEARD OF
HAPPY THE CAT-MANDER.
BRACE YOURSELF,
'CAUSE HE'S RIGHT HERE.
SHE LOVES ME!
THIS MUST BE DESTINY!
- DESTINED TO BE REJECTED--
SHE'S TOTALLY IGNORING YOU.
- NAIVE COMMENTS LIKE THAT
PROVE YOU KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT WOMEN
AND THEIR WILD WAYS.
- I REALLY HATE
TO BREAK THIS TO YOU,
BUT I'M A WOMAN!
- THAT GIRL'S GONNA BE
GORGEOUS WHEN SHE GROWS UP.
- DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
HIBIKI WANTS TO WAIT.
- WOULD YOU PLEASE
COME WITH ME, LOVELY LADY?
- UM, OKAY.
- BAD TOUCH!
- HMM...
- YOU SENSED IT TOO.
THAT GIRL'S PARFUM
IS QUITE UNIQUE.
SHE IS NO ORDINARY CHILD.
- I SENSED THAT ABOUT HER
RIGHT AWAY.
THE MAGIC SHE POSSESSES IS
SOMEHOW DIFFERENT FROM OUR OWN.
IT SEEMS LADY ERZA
HAS NOTICED HER POWER AS WELL.
- IMPRESSIVE.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- WE'RE PAMPERING A PRINCESS.
- YOU'RE THE CUTEST GIRL
I'VE SEEN ALL DAY.
- WOULD YOU LIKE TO FRESHEN UP?
- ( Wendy gasps )
PLEASE HELP ME.
- JUST WHAT DO YOU
EXPECT ME TO DO?
- ( chuckles nervously )
- HMM...
- WOW. THINKING MUST BE PAINFUL.
- IT'S SO WEIRD. I FEEL
LIKE I'VE HEARD THAT
LITTLE GIRL'S NAME BEFORE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHERE.
- YEAH?
- GIVE IT A REST.
IT HURTS JUST WATCHING YOU.
- HEY, CAN YOU REMEMBER HER
FOR ME?
- SAY WHAT?!
- IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
WE CAN DO FOR YOU,
LOVELY PRINCESS?
- ( giggles )
- ( sighs )
SO, YOU GOT ANYTHING YET?
- WORKING ON IT.
- IT'S UN-LADYLIKE TO SMILE
AT STRANGE MEN, WENDY.
- BUT I WAS JUST BEING FRIENDLY!
- AHH...
- DO YOU LIKE YOUR MEN
BRASH OR PROPER?
- BRASH, RIGHT?
- YOU ARE JUST THE CUTEST.
- I TOLD YOU THREE,
THEY'RE HERE ON BUSINESS!
NOW CLEAN THIS PLACE UP!
- YES, DEAR MASTER, RIGHT AWAY!
- MAN...
- THOSE PRETTY BOYS KEEP
CALLING HIM DIFFERENT THINGS.
- THEY MAY NOT BE
THE BRIGHTEST,
BUT AT LEAST THEY'RE
CONSISTENTLY INCONSISTENT.
- OKAY, NOW THAT ALL THE
INVOLVED PARTIES ARE PRESENT,
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME TO GET
THE MISSION BRIEFING UNDERWAY.
- Lucy: YOU'RE GONNA BRIEF US
THROUGH INTERPRETIVE DANCE?
- OUR FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS,
IS DETERMINING THE LOCATION
OF THE ORACION SEIS.
- ( deeply sighs )
- RIGHT AFTER I MAKE
A LETTER OF THE ALPHABET.
- GREAT. IF HE'S MAKING THE
LETTER "POOP," I'M OUTTA HERE.
- WE'RE ROOTING
FOR YOU, TEACHER!
- PICK A TITLE, WOULD YOU?!
- PIRI PIRI!
- MUCH BETTER. NOW, PLEASE,
PAY CLOSE ATTENTION.
TO THE NORTH LIES
THE WORTH WOODSEA,
WHERE THE ANCIENTS ONCE
SEALED A POWERFUL FORCE.
A MAGIC CALLED NIRVANA!
- THOSE POSES ARE
GETTING REALLY OLD.
- Both: NIRVANA?
- ( slightly gasps )
- NEVER HEARD OF IT BEFORE.
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
- NO.  I DO NOT.
- THIS CONVERSATION'S
BORING, HUH?
WANNA NOM ON MY MACKEREL?
- HEAVENS NO!
- WE DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT THIS MAGIC,
OTHER THAN ITS NAME.
AND THAT IT IS DESTRUCTIVE
IN NATURE.
- AND THAT THE ORACION SEIS
WANTS IT BADLY.
- DESTRUCTION MAGIC...
- OKAY, BAD FEELING CONFIRMED.
- MM.
- WE ASSUME THAT'S WHY THEY
TRAVELED TO THE WORTH WOODSEA.
THEY'RE DESPERATE TO GET THEIR
HANDS ON SUCH A POWERFUL MAGIC.
- TO PREVENT THAT
FROM HAPPENING...
All: WE MUST DESTROY
THE ORACION SEIS!
- I'M SO OVER THE POSING.
- I THINK THEY'RE STARTING
TO GROW ON ME.
- WE MAY HAVE THE ADVANTAGE
IN NUMBERS,
BUT REMEMBER...
- WE CANNOT UNDERESTIMATE THEM.
- THEY'RE INCREDIBLY STRONG.
WE MAY WELL BE IN
OVER OUR HEADS.
- Jura: THAT'S ARCHIVE.
- Lyon: DON'T BELIEVE
I'VE SEEN IT IN USE BEFORE.
- Sherry:
AND IT DOES WHAT EXACTLY?
- STORING INFORMATION,
SUCH AS THESE PHOTOGRAPHS
OF OUR ENEMY.
DON'T ASK HOW WE GOT 'EM.
FIRST UP IS
THE SNAKE WIZARD. COBRA.
- BEADY EYES AND
A MISCHIEVOUS SMIRK.
HE LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE TO ME.
- TALK ABOUT THE POT
CALLING THE KETTLE BLACK.
- Hibiki: NEXT IS A WIZARD
WHO, JUDGING FROM HIS NAME,
LIKELY USES SPEED MAGIC.
MEET RACER.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT I DON'T LIKE THE
LOOKS OF THIS GUY.
- I DON'T EITHER.
- Hibiki: THEN THERE'S A WIZARD
WHO'S WILLING TO WIPE OUT
AN ENTIRE MILITARY UNIT,
IF THE PRICE IS RIGHT.
"DIVINE EYES" HOTEYE.
- THE GUY KILLS FOR MONEY?
- TURNS MY STOMACH.
- Hibiki: SHE'S GORGEOUS,
BUT JUST AS VICIOUS.
THIS IS ANGEL.
- SHE'S THE BEAUTIFUL
BUT DEADLY TYPE, HUH?
IS THIS CHICK FOR REAL?
- Hibiki: THE NEXT MEMBER
IS SUCH A MYSTERY,
ALL WE KNOW IS HIS NAME--
MIDNIGHT.
- THAT'S AN ODD NAME.
DOES IT CORRELATE TO HIS POWER?
- Hibiki: FINALLY, THE
COMMANDER OF ORACION SEIS.
BRAIN.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
ALONE THEY CAN WIPE OUT
ENTIRE GUILDS,
AND TOGETHER,
THEY'RE UNSTOPPABLE.
WE HAVE 12 TO THEIR SIX,
BUT THAT'S OUR ONLY ADVANTAGE.
- QUESTION-- CAN I VOLUNTEER TO
STAY BEHIND AND NOT DIE TODAY?
- I DON'T WANNA DIE EITHER,
SO MAY I PLEASE GO HOME?
- YOU MAY NOT!
WE HAVE A JOB TO DO, CHILD.
- SINCE THEY DIDN'T COUNT US,
YOU WANNA GET OUT OF HERE,
AND FIND SOME TRASH CANS
TO RAID?
- ( huffs )
- CURB YOUR FEAR, MY FRIENDS.
THERE IS MORE TO OUR OPERATION
THAN MORTAL COMBAT.
WITH YOUR HELP, PERHAPS WE CAN
FIND THE ENEMY'S STRONGHOLD.
- STRONGHOLD?
- YEAH, YOU HEARD THE MAN.
WE'VE LOOKED EVERYWHERE,
BUT HAVE HAD NO LUCK.
- HERE'S THE DEAL: THEY'VE
GOTTA HAVE A TEMPORARY BASE
IN THE WORTH WOODSEA.
- AND ONCE WE'VE LOCATED IT,
OUR PLAN IS TO GATHER
THE ORACION SEIS INSIDE.
- HOW DO WE DO THAT?
- WE BEAT 'EM UP
AND DRAG THEIR BUTTS THERE!
- HE'S A LITTLE
TOO EXCITED ABOUT THIS.
- WHAT'S THE NEXT PART
OF THE PLAN?
- THEN WE'LL GIVE THEM
A ONE-WAY TICKET TO OBLIVION!
COURTESY OF CHRISTINA,
THE MAJESTIC PRIDE
OF THE BLUE PEGASUS GUILD.
- I'VE HEARD ABOUT
THE MAGIC BOMBER,
BUT I THOUGHT
IT WAS JUST A MYTH.
- WHOA!  IS THAT NECESSARY?
THERE'S ONLY SIX OF 'EM.
- THAT'S THE TYPE
OF ENEMY WE FACE.
- SIR, YES, SIR!
- REMEMBER:
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE
SHOULD YOU EVER ENGAGE
THE ENEMY IN SOLO COMBAT.
OUR BEST BET
IS TO SEPARATE THEM,
THEN DEVOTE TWO WIZARDS
TO EACH FIGHT.
- ( all grunt in agreement )
- OH!  THIS IS
A TOTAL NIGHTMARE!
- I CAN'T TAKE THE PRESSURE.
- WOULD YOU TWO STOP
ACTING LIKE CHILDREN?
- LET'S GO!
I'M ALL FIRED UP!
TIME TO HUNT ME SOME DEMONS.
READY OR NOT,
HERE I COME!
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?!
- ALWAYS ACTING
WITHOUT A THOUGHT IN HIS HEAD.
- SOME DAYS I WONDER
ABOUT HIS MENTAL HEALTH.
- WHAT DO YOU GUYS WANNA BET
HE DIDN'T EVEN HEAR THE PLAN?
- I'LL BET FIVE FISH HE DIDN'T.
- OVERKILL MUCH?
- YEAH, NO KIDDING.
- JUST GREAT.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIX IT.
- ENOUGH GAWKING.
MOVE.
- GUESS WE'RE PLAYING CATCH-UP
WITH THAT DORK.
- AWW!  DO WE HAVE TO?
- DOUBLE TIME IT!
- QUIT CRYING!
- THEIR ENERGY'S AS INFECTIOUS
AS I REMEMBER.
READY, SHERRY?
- YEAH!
- WAIT, STAY TOGETHER.
- SO WE'RE HUNTING DEMONS?
- MM-HMM.
- AND AN ANGEL TOO.
- ( murmurs )
- PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER, CHILD!
- HAVE NO FEAR!
'CAUSE THE CAT-MANDER'S HERE!
- YOU'LL BE THE DEATH OF ME.
- SORRY, CARLA.
- ( murmurs )
WAIT FOR ME!
YOU NEED A MAN
TO PROTECT YOU!
- I'M TOO OLD FOR THIS.
- MAN...
- IN ANY CASE, THE OPERATION
IS NOW UNDERWAY.
WE SHOULD JOIN
THE OTHERS QUICKLY.
- SLOW YOUR ROLL, SHINY DOME.
I'VE HEARD THROUGH
THE GRAPEVINE
THAT YOU'RE ONE OF
THE 10 WIZARD SAINTS.
WOULD THIS STATEMENT BE TRUE?
- INDEED, I AM.
- IT'S QUITE A PRIVILEGE
TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE
SOMEONE AS SKILLED
AS MASTER MAKAROV.
- I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR.
THOUGH I AM HONORED TO
BEAR THE TITLE,
IT IS GIVEN TO WHOMEVER
THE COUNCIL DEEMS WORTHY.
EQUATING MYSELF WITH MAKAROV
IS TANTAMOUNT
TO COMPARING
THE HEAVENS TO THE EARTH.
I'M SURE YOU CAN GUESS
WHICH APPLIES TO ME.
- I SEE.
THAT MIGHT BE THE BEST
NEWS I'VE HEARD ALL DAY.
IF YOU WERE AS POWERFUL
AS THAT FOSSIL,
IT WOULD MAKE MY JOB
FAR MORE DIFFICULT.
- ( groans )
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
AAH!
( gags, coughs )
- THIS PARTICULAR PARFUM
CAUSES AN OPPONENT TO LOSE
THEIR WILL TO FIGHT.
- ( groaning, coughing )
ICHIYA, WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
- PIRI PIRI...
- ( groans )
AAH!
- THAT'S MORE LIKE IT. DROWN IN
RELENTLESS PAIN AND TORMENT.
ARE YOU ENJOYING THE POTENT
EFFECTS OF MY LITTLE FRAGRANCE?
- AAH!
- OOPS, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
I MEANT PARFUM!
- WE'RE BACK TO NORMAL!
- YUCK, THAT MIDGET'S HEAD
WAS FILLED WITH PERVERTED STUFF.
- DON'T REMIND ME, BROTHER.
GROWN-UPS CAN BE SO GROSS.
- NO COMPLAINING.
YOU'RE NOT DONE YET.
- PIRI PIRI...
- NO, NOT YOU!
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- OH, ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
YOU'VE BEEN DUPED, DARLING.
WE COPIED YOUR COMRADE--
FROM HIS DUMPY LITTLE BODY
TO EVERY THOUGHT
IN HIS PERVERTED MIND.
- NOW WE KNOW YOUR PLAN.
- YOU CAN'T HIDE
ANYTHING FROM US.
- NO...
- YES.
TWO DOWN,
AND ONLY 10 TO GO.
- ( groaning )
- ( groans )
- PIRI PIRI...
- ( laughs )
LET THIS BE A LESSON TO YOU,
CHILDREN OF LIGHT,
THERE'S NO STOPPING
THE ORACION SEIS.
- THERE IT IS.
- WAIT UP, NUMBSKULL!
- YEAH, IN YOUR DREAMS.
- THAT'S AN ORDER!
YOU CAN'T RUSH INTO
THIS ONE ALONE.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU AFRAID
I MIGHT ACTUALLY
SHOW YOU UP THIS TIME?
- SAY WHAT?!
STOP MOVING YOUR FEET
RIGHT NOW!
- I WAS JUST KIDDING AROUND!
AAH!
- WELL, HE STOPPED
MOVING HIS FEET.
- IF HE'S NOT DEAD,
I'LL KILL HIM.
- I SEE HE HASN'T CHANGED
AT ALL.
- TO THINK, I ONCE CROSSED
FISTS WITH THAT FOOL.
IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING NOW.
- IT'S ANOTHER FORM
OF LOVE.
- YEAH, NOT QUITE.
- WAHH!  I CAN'T BELIEVE
THOSE JERKS RAN OFF
AND LEFT ME TO FEND
FOR MYSELF.
WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO LADIES FIRST, HUH?
- A GEM LIKE YOU
SHOULD BE TREATED WITH CARE.
- WHAT CAN I DO
TO MAKE YOU SMILE, DEAR?
- STAY AT MY SIDE,
THAT'S AN ORDER.
- CREEPY!
- QUIT LOLLYGAGGING, WENDY.
HURRY UP!
- I'M TRYING.
- HAPPY'S AIR SERVICE CAN HELP!
- ( groans )
MY HEAD'S KILLING ME.
WHAT'S WITH THIS FOREST?
IT SURE HAS A FUNKY SMELL TO IT.
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT HERE.
- NO KIDDING.
IT'S LIKE THE DEEPER
WE GO INTO IT,
THE SPOOKIER IT GETS.
- KEEP YOUR GUARD UP,
UNDERSTAND?
- YEAH.
- Natsu:
YOU FINALLY CAUGHT UP.
- YOU'RE ONE STURDY FREAK,
YOU KNOW THAT?
- WHOA!
AAH!
SO WE'RE PULLING
CHEAP SHOTS NOW, ARE WE?!
- IF I WANTED A PIECE OF YOU,
I'D TAKE YOU HEAD-ON.
- FOCUS!
- Gray and Natsu:
WHOA!
- Sherry: LYON?
- I SEE IT.
- Erza:
THAT'S THE MAGIC BOMBER--
CHRISTINA.
- Natsu: I WANT ONE!
- Gray: IT DEFINITELY
LIVES UP TO THE HYPE.
- WHOA...
- THAT'S SO COOL.
- HORSES CAN FLY TOO?
- PLEASE REFRAIN FROM
OPENING YOUR MOUTH AGAIN.
- Erza:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SPLIT UP
AND START SEARCHING FOR
THEIR TEMPORARY BASE.
- Natsu:
I'M FLYING THE BOMBER THING!
- Gray:
NOT HAPPENING.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH CHRISTINA?
- OH, NO!
- THIS DOESN'T BODE WELL.
- ( sniffs )
GRAY.
- I KNOW.
WE'VE GOT COMPANY.
EVERYONE STAY FROSTY.
- I CAN'T DO THIS.
- DON'T HIDE!
- YEAH, IT'S GOTTA BE THEM.
THE ORACION SEIS.
- LOWLY MAGGOTS
SWARMING TOGETHER.
- I'M AFRAID SHORT-STUFF ISN'T
GOING TO MAKE IT TO THE PARTY.
- AND NEITHER IS THAT
BIG, BALD WIZARD SAINT.
- WE TOOK 'EM DOWN!
- THEY'RE DEFEATED?
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- THERE'S TERROR
IN THEIR VOICES.
I CAN HEAR IT.
- THE QUICKER WE WRAP THIS UP,
THE BETTER.
I'LL RUN YOU OVER SO FAST,
IT'LL MAKE YOUR HEAD SPIN.
- MONEY DETERMINES STRENGTH
IN THIS WORLD.
OH, YEAH!  IF YOU SAVE
BUT A PENNY TODAY,
IT SHALL BECOME
A VAST FORTUNE IN THE FUTURE.
FURTHERMORE--
- ENOUGH WITH THE
PREACHING, HOTEYE.
- ( snoring )
- IS IT SAD THAT I'M TERRIFIED
OF THE SNORING GUY?
- I HAVE TO ADMIT, I DIDN'T
EXPECT YOU TO SHOW YOURSELVES.
- ( bones crack )
- READY?
- YOU BET.
- ( chuckles )
WANT AN INVITATION?
- Both: YOU BEING HERE
IS ENOUGH FOR US!
- TAKE THEM.
- YES, SIR.
MOTOR!
- Both: NATSU, GRAY!
HUH?
- SURPRISE!
- WHY AM I WHIPPING MYSELF?!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
( sobs )
- ( chuckles )
- SHERRY!
- RIGHT!
- I SEE YOU!
OH, YEAH!
FORGET LOVE;
ALL YOU NEED IS MONEY.
MONEY'S ALL YOU NEED.
- WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
QUICKSAND?
- HOW DARE HE SAY
LOVE IS LESS IMPORTANT?
GRAB MY HAND, LOVE!
- I'LL TAKE CARE OF ANGEL.
- HEY, NO DIBS!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "TAKE CARE"?
- ( whirring )
- AAH!
- REN!
AAH!
- EVE, YOU OKAY?
HOW?  HE'S SO FAST.
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE IT.
- IF YOU'RE SLOW,
YOU'LL BE EATING MY DUST.
- REQUIP!
- THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
- DANCE, MY SWORDS!
PIERCE AND REND!
NO...
HE DODGED THEM ALL.
CAN HE READ MY ATTACKS?
- ( pants )
COME ON.
- ( snoring )
- SERIOUSLY?!
QUIT SAWING LOGS
AND PUT UP YOUR STUPID FISTS!
- REQUIP!
FLIGHT ARMOR!
( grunts )
- THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
YEAH.  I LIKE FAST WOMEN.
- IT'S NO USE.
I CAN HEAR YOUR NEXT MOVE,
TITANIA.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
GIVE UP NOW!
- HE IS READING ME.
BUT HOW?!
- YOU LOOK CONFUSED.
HAVING TROUBLE FIGURING IT OUT?
I TOLD YOU,
I HEAR EVERYTHING.
- WAKEY WAKEY!
WHAT?!  YOU GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME!
HE SHOULD BE BARBECUED
RIGHT NOW.
- CAREFUL.
- ( grunts )
- IF YOU WAKE HIM UP,
IT'S GONNA BE YOUR NIGHTMARE!
- AAH!
- ICE MAKE LANCE!
- DITTO!
- ICE MAKE EAGLE!
- MARIONETTE ATTACK!
MUD DOLL!
- MONEY WILL TRIUMPH OVER ALL!
OH, YEAH!
- ( Sherry and Lyon scream )
- ( grunting )
- I SEE.
THIS IS THE FAMED
ERZA SCARLET.
- I CAN HEAR IT ALL, YOU KNOW?
IT'S LIKE A SYMPHONY.
YOUR MUSCLES CONTRACTING
EVERY BREATH THAT YOU TAKE IN,
AND ALL YOUR THOUGHTS.
( gasps )
WHAT THE--?
YOU WERE THERE?
- HE'S OPEN!
AAH!
- I SAW THAT!
OH, YEAH!
- COBRA!
PICK UP THE THE PACE, WILL YOU?
- CUBELLIOS!
- ( grunts, screams )
- YOU MAY BE FAST,
BUT THAT WON'T SAVE YOU
FROM CUBELLIOS' POISON.
ENJOY WRITHING IN AGONY
TILL DEATH CLAIMS YOU.
- ( all groaning )
- HOW PATHETIC.
PREPARE FOR OBLIVION'S EMBRACE.
- WHAT IS THIS MAGIC?
IT FEELS DARK...
- I CAN'T MOVE ANYMORE.
- ME NEITHER.
- DARK RONDO!
- ( whimpers )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, BRAIN?
- ARE YOU GONNA CAST
THAT THING OR WHAT?
- ( exhales )
WENDY...
- YEAH?
- (end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: WOW, ORACION SEIS IS
SUPER-STRONG.
YOU GUYS SURE GOT
YOUR BUTTS WHOOPED GOOD.
- Natsu: LYING ON THE GROUND
IS PART OF MY STRATEGY.
- WELL, THE "LYING" PART
IS TRUE, AT LEAST.
- I HAVEN'T LOST
UNTIL I SAY I HAVE.
ONCE I'M ON MY FEET,
THEY'RE GOING DOWN IN FLAMES!
- AND YOU'LL GET BEAT AGAIN,
JUST LIKE ALL YOUR REMATCHES.
IT'S A VICIOUS CYCLE.
- ( Natsu and Happy speaking )
- Natsu: WHEN HAVE I EVER
LOST A REMATCH?!
- Happy: SERIOUSLY?!
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?!
- ( scoffs ) I ALWAYS THOUGHT
OF THOSE AS DRAWS.
- MUST BE NICE
LIVING IN TOTAL DELUSION.