Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Ichiya:
ICHIYA OF BLUE PEGASUS
AND HIS ADORING MINIONS
THE TRIMEN
CLAIMED VICTORY
OVER THE ORACION SEIS.
NOW THE DARING ICHIYA
MUST TAKE LEAVE
OF HIS BELOVED HONEY MISS ERZA
TO FIGHT FOR THE HOPES AND
DREAMS OF NOT ONLY HIS COMRADES,
BUT OF ALL MANKIND.
- Happy: REALLY PLAYING
YOURSELF UP THERE, PAL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
THE MUCH SOUGHT AFTER NIRVANA
IS A POWERFUL SPELL CAPABLE
OF SWITCHING LIGHT
AND DARKNESS.
ITS CREATORS THE NIRVITS,
FEARFUL OF ITS POWER,
SEALED IT AWAY
A LONG TIME AGO.
THEIR DESCENDANTS
BANDED TOGETHER
TO FORM THE CAIT
SHELTER GUILD.
NOW THE ORACION SEIS'
MASTER ZERO IS USING
THE NIRVITS' CREATION
AGAINST THEM,
AS HE HAS NIRVANA AIMED DIRECTLY
AT THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD HALL.
NATSU AND THE OTHERS MUST DO
EVERYTHING IN THEIR POWER
TO STOP MASTER ZERO
BEFORE TIME RUNS OUT.
- Natsu: I CAN FEEL MY FRIENDS'
DETERMINATION AND STRENGTH
PULSATING THROUGH ME!
- I SHALL RETURN YOU
TO THE NOTHINGNESS
FROM WHENCE YOU CAME.
- DRAGON SLAYER SECRET ART!
FLAME LOTUS,
EXPLODING FLAME BLADE!
- ( Happy speaking )
- IT'S GO TIME.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.  LET'S DO THIS.
- OPEN, GATE OF THE GOLDEN BULL.
TAURUS!
- GO, COW!
- ( roaring )
- WE'RE BOTH COUNTING
ON YOU, TAURUS.
- MOO!  IF I DO THIS,
DO I GET A SMOOCH
FROM THE TWO OF YOU?
- ( roars )
POWER PARFUM
TO THE MAX.
MAN!
- REQUIP.
BLACK WING ARMOR.
HERE WE GO.
- GRANDINA,
LEND ME YOUR STRENGTH.
- WENDY, I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT
IF YOU JUST STAY FOCUSED.
- ( screaming )
HISTORY WILL COME TO AN END
BEFORE MY EYES.
A NEW ERA OF NOTHINGNESS
SHALL BE USHERED IN.
GENESIS ZERO.
NOW OPEN,
PORTAL OF THE DEMON'S WAIL.
GO TRAVELERS OF THE VOID.
I WANT YOU TO CONSUME THAT
MAN'S SOUL AND HIS MEMORY.
CONSUME HIS VERY EXISTENCE.
DEVOUR HIM.
DO IT FOR THE SAKE
OF YOUR MASTER.
- ( screaming )
- AND NOW, YOU TOO,
ARE A TRAVELER
OF THE INFINITE VOID.
GOODBYE, DRAGON SLAYER.
WHAT THE-- THIS SUCKS.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING,
AND I'M ALL OUT OF POWER.
WHAT'LL I DO?
- Igneel:
NATSU, WHAT HAPPENED?
HOW COULD YOU ALLOW HIM
TO DEFEAT YOU SO EASILY?
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
AND YOU CALL YOURSELF
THE SON OF IGNEEL?
- AW, COME ON, YOU DON'T
REALLY EXPECT ME TO SHATTER
THAT HUGE ROCK ALL BY MYSELF,
DO YOU?
- I'M NOT ASKING THE IMPOSSIBLE
OF YOU, MY BOY.
I KNOW YOU HAVE THE POWER TO
DO IT.  STOP DOUBTING YOURSELF.
- NEVER FORGET YOU ARE
A TRUE DRAGON SLAYER
AND YOU SHOULD TAKE PRIDE
IN THAT ACCOMPLISHMENT.
KNOW THAT NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS,
I, IGNEEL,
WILL ALWAYS BE PROUD OF YOU.
- OKAY, I'LL TRY AGAIN.
BUT I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
- LET'S GO, ICE CANNON!
- HERE WE GO!
- GO!
- INFINITY SPARKLE!
- ONLY HAVE ONE CHANCE, SO I'LL
PUT ALL OF MY REMAINING POWER
INTO THIS GLOVE.
( yells )
- SKY DRAGON ROAR!
- NO, IT CAN'T BE.
- ( explosion )
- HOW DID HE COME BACK
FROM THE VOID?
SUCH BRILLIANT GOLDEN FLAMES.
MY MAGIC IS BEING BURNT AWAY.
( screaming )
Zero: HIS LOST MAGIC GIVES HIM
THE POWER OF A DRAGON
AND IN TURN,
THE POWER TO DEFEAT ONE.
THIS BOY IS A TRUE
DRAGON SLAYER.
- I'M DONE PLAYING GAMES
WITH YOU, PAL.
DRAGON SLAYER SECRET ART.
HIDDEN FIRE FORM.
FLAME LOTUS PHOENIX SWORD!
- ( screaming )
- ( clamoring )
- GUESS THIS MEANS IT WORKED.
WE HIT ALL OF 'EM
AT THE SAME TIME.
- WE DID IT!
- ( cheering )
- AWW, YEAH!
- PERFECT TIMING.
WE DID IT.
GOOD JOB, EVERYONE.
- THANKS TO YOU, NATSU.
- ( gasps )
- Natsu:
THAT WAS ROUGH.
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT ONE LACRIMA
WOULD BE SO HARD TO BREAK?
( coughs )
NO MORE DOUBTING MYSELF.
THANK YOU, IGNEEL.
- ( laughing )
- I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, WENDY.
CAIT SHELTER HAS BEEN SAVED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WE STOPPED NIRVANA.
- ( snickers )
- NATSU DRAGNEEL.
AMAZING.
HE'S EXCEEDED MY EXPECTATIONS.
- AW, CRAP.
I'M ALL OUT OF MAGIC ENERGY.
( shouting )
THAT WAS CLOSE.
- I'VE GOT YOU.
- FOR NOW ANYWAY.
THIS SPELLS TROUBLE
FOR YOU, TOO, YOU KNOW?
- PROBABLY NOT A VERY
GOOD SIGN, IS IT?
- THIS PLACE IS FALLING APART.
- I'D MAKE A RUN FOR IT
IF I WERE YOU.
- YOU'RE GONNA GET SQUISHED
IF YOU STICK AROUND.
- DO YOU KNOW IF THERE'S SOME
KIND OF EMERGENCY EXIT?
- WE'RE NOT ALL-KNOWING.
WE CAN ONLY READ THE THOUGHTS
OF THE PEOPLE WE'VE COPIED.
- AND NONE OF THEM KNEW ANYTHING
ABOUT ABOUT EMERGENCY EXITS.
- YOU'LL FIND YOUR WAY
OUT OF HERE SOMEHOW.
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU.
- Both: DON'T GO.
- AWW, MAN, THIS IS BAD.
WE GOTTA GET OUT
OF THIS DUMP NOW.
- I HOPE EVERYONE'S ALL RIGHT.
- WAIT, MY HONEY.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE
YOUR LOVE BEHIND.
( grunting )
- SLOW DOWN, CARLA.
I CAN'T KEEP UP.
- WE'VE GOT TO MOVE QUICKLY,
CHILD.
- OH!
- ( gasps )
- OW!
- WENDY!
- LOOK OUT!
- Jura: IRON ROCK WALL!
- ( screaming )
YOU SAVED US.
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE
AS GOOD AS DEAD.
- I SIMPLY NEEDED SOME TIME
TO RECUPERATE,
RESTORE MY MAGIC ENERGY.
WE HAVE TO HURRY.
NIRVANA'S RAPIDLY COLLAPSING.
- ( screaming )
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
IT'S GOING DOWN FAST.
HOPE THE OTHERS MADE IT OUT.
- GRAY.
- ERZA.
AND...
- I'M SO GLAD YOU MADE IT
OUT SAFELY,
MY BLAZON-HAIRED BEAUTY.
- ( shrieking )
- WHO ARE YOU?
- YOU HEARD HER.
ANSWER THE LADY OR ELSE.
- PLEASE CALM DOWN.
CAN'T YOU SEE I'M YOUR ALLY?
MY POWER PARFUM HAS TEMPORARILY
ALTERED MY OUTWARD APPEARANCE.
BUT DEEP DOWN,
I HAVEN'T CHANGED.
( laughs )
I'M YOUR BELOVED ICHIYA,
AND YOU'RE MY HONEY.
LOOK AT ME SPARKLE.
- LOOKS LIKE YOUR 'LIL ADMIRER'S
GONE FULL-ON STALKER.
- NO JOKE.  I'D KICK HIM OUT
OF THE ALLIANCE,
BUT HE'S SO DEPENDABLE.
- ( yawning )
"SO DIZZY,"
SHE SAYS IN A WARBLED TONE.
- AN ENEMY.
- NO, STAND DOWN.
- YEAH, IT'S JUST ONE
OF LUCY'S SPIRITS.
- THANKS FOR SAVING US,
HOROLOGIUM.
BUT I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER
SUMMONING YOU.
- YOU DIDN'T.  I PASSED THROUGH
THE GATE OF MY OWN ACCORD.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
- YOU CAN RESCUE US ANY TIME
YOU FEEL LIKE IT.
THANKS.
- MISS LUCY'S MAGIC IS
GETTING STRONGER BY THE DAY,
SO IT'S LIKELY YOU'LL SEE
MORE CELESTIAL SPIRITS
DOING THE SAME.
THAT SAID, I'M MORE USEFUL THAN
THE OTHERS, AS I CAN PREVENT
OXYGEN DEPRIVATION,
INSECT BITES, INFLAMMATION
AND BLEMISHES.
- NO WAY.  HE PREVENTS ACNE?
- DIDN'T KNOW THAT WAS
A PROBLEM FOR YOU.
- MY IDENTITY IS BEING
THREATENED AGAIN
AND I DON'T LIKE IT ONE BIT.
- THANK GOODNESS.
EVERYONE'S ALL RIGHT.
- EVEN THAT SILLY BLUE TOMCAT.
- NATSU AND JELLAL.
ARE THEY HERE?
- I DON'T SEE THEM.
- CARLA!
- COULD THEY BOTH BE INSIDE?
- Wendy: I HOPE NOT.
- NOW I'M WORRIED.
- HE'S PROBABLY LOST
IN THE WOODSEA,
KNOWING THAT FLAME-FOR-BRAINS.
- HEY, NATSU!
- NATSU.  JELLAL.
I KNOW YOU'RE OUT THERE.
- WHERE ARE YOU, BUDDY?
WHOA!
- LOVE DRIVES US TO SAVE
OUR FRIENDS.  OH, YEAH!
- THERE HE IS.  ALWAYS
WITH THE DRAMATIC ENTRANCE.
- YOU'RE OKAY.
- WHAT ON EARTH
IS HE DOING HERE?
HE'S ONE OF
THE ORACION SEIS, ISN'T HE?
- YES, BUT HE'S ON OUR SIDE NOW.
IT'S A LONG STORY.
I'LL EXPLAIN LATER.
- ( laughing ) NATSU!
YOU KEPT YOUR PROMISE.
YOU'RE THE GREATEST.
I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
- ( laughs )
- IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU, CAIT
SHELTER WOULD'VE BEEN WIPED OUT.
- WELL, THERE'S NO WAY
I COULD'VE DONE IT ON MY OWN.
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
- YOU SAVED MY GUILD.
- NO, WE SAVED YOUR GUILD.
- MAN!
- Wendy:
I DIDN'T DO MUCH.
- COME ON, YOU DESTROYED
A LACRIMA, TOO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- Happy: I'M GLAD EVERYONE MADE
IT OUT OF THERE OKAY.
- IT WAS CLOSE.
EXCELLENT WORK BY ALL INVOLVED.
- I THINK IT'S TIME FOR A GROUP
HUG.  WHO'S WITH ME?
- FORGET IT, CREEP.
- HEY.
SPEAKING OF CREEPS, WHO'S THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- ANOTHER PRETTY BOY
FROM BLUE PEGASUS?
- WOULDN'T WE HAVE
MET HIM EARLIER?
- Erza: IT'S JELLAL.
- YOU KIDDING ME?
- OH, NO, NOT HIM AGAIN.
- Erza: HE'S CHANGED.
HE'S NOT THE SAME MAN WE DEALT
WITH BEFORE.
- Wendy:
HE'S COMPLETELY LOST HIS MEMORY.
- REALLY?  I STILL DON'T THINK
WE CAN TRUST THE GUY.
- YOU CAN, I PROMISE.
I'M TELLING YOU,
HE'S ACTUALLY A GOOD PERSON.
- I WANTED TO THANK YOU.
HONESTLY, WE COULDN'T HAVE
DONE THIS WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
- ERZA.  THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WORTHY
OF SUCH PRAISE.
NOT AT ALL.
- SO TELL ME,
WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
- GOOD QUESTION.
I WISH I KNEW.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.  I'M SURE
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
IN THAT POSITION.
WHO KNOWS WHAT TOMORROW
MIGHT HAVE IN STORE?
- I'M AFRAID.
- OF WHAT?
- MY MEMORY.
OF IT RETURNING.
- DON'T BE.
IT WOULDN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
EVEN IF WE WERE TO BECOME
ENEMIES AGAIN,
IT WOULDN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT I CARE ABOUT YOU.
- YOU DO?
- MORE THAN YOU KNOW.
- Ichiya: MY HANDSOME FACE!
- Natsu: HUH?
- Gray:
THERE A PROBLEM, MEATHEAD?
- I WANTED TO GO MAKE A LETTER
OF THE ALPHABET,
BUT I RAN
INTO AN INVISIBLE WALL.
- LOOK.  THERE'S WEIRD WRITING
ON THE GROUND.
- NO, IT CAN'T BE.
- All: AN ENCHANTMENT?
- Ichiya: MAN!
I'VE REALLY GOTTA PEE,
YOU GUYS.
- WHO'D DO SUCH A THING?
- AND HOW COME WE DIDN'T
NOTICE WHO CAST IT?
- IF I HAD TO GUESS,
I'D SAY IT'S FREED'S WORK.
STRIKE THAT.
THIS MAGIC IS MUCH MORE POWERFUL
THAN HIS COULD EVER BE.
- OH, GREAT,
HOW ARE WE GONNA GET OUT?
- OKAY, WHO DID THIS?
SHOW YOURSELF.
- WHO ARE ALL THESE PEOPLE?
- ( grunting ) LET ME GO PEE.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO PANIC.
WE MEAN YOU NO HARM.
SORRY ABOUT THIS,
BUT WE WERE FORCED
TO DO SOMETHING
TO RESTRAIN YOU.
- WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
- I AM THE CAPTAIN
OF THE NEW MAGIC COUNCIL'S
FOURTH CUSTODY
ENFORCEMENT UNIT-- LAHAR.
AND THIS IS MY ARMY.
- WHAT?
- THERE'S A NEW MAGIC COUNCIL?
- SURE DIDN'T
TAKE 'EM VERY LONG.
IT IS MY DUTY TO UPHOLD THE LAW
AND PRESERVE JUSTICE
THROUGHOUT THE LAND.
SO ALL EVILDOERS
MUST BE ARRESTED.
- WE'RE NOT EVILDOERS.
- I DON'T GET WHY WE'RE
IN TROUBLE WHEN WE DIDN'T
EVEN DO ANYTHING WRONG.
- LEAST, NOT THAT WE KNOW OF.
- THAT'S NOT GONNA SELL HIM
ON OUR INNOCENCE, NATSU.
- I'M NOT HERE TO ARREST YOU.
I HAVE BEEN ORDERED TO TAKE
THE ORACION SEIS INTO CUSTODY.
I ASK THAT YOU PLEASE COOPERATE
AND HAND OVER THE MEMBER
CODENAMED "HOTEYE."
- ( gasping )
- NO, NEVER!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SURRENDER.
- RICHARD, WHY?
- I CANNOT FULLY EMBRACE A LIFE
OF VIRTUE
WHEN MY PAST TRANSGRESSIONS
CONTINUE TO HAUNT ME.
THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO ATONE FOR MY SINS.
IT'S BEST THAT I HAVE A CLEAN
SLATE WHEN I FIND MY BROTHER.
THAT WAY, I WILL HAVE
NOTHING TO HIDE.
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- INDEED, MAY I CONTINUE
THE SEARCH FOR YOUR BROTHER
IN YOUR STEAD?
- YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
- I WOULD BE HONORED.
I JUST NEED HIS NAME.
HIS NAME IS WALLY.
WALLY BUCHANAN.
- HUH?
- HE'S YOUR BROTHER?
- DANDY.
- THE BLOCKHEAD?
- I MISS HIM DEARLY.
HE WAS A GOOD KID.
IN FACT, HE WAS THE BEST LITTLE
BROTHER A GUY COULD ASK FOR.
- JEEZ, THIS SOIL'S HARD.
- I KNOW BUT WE'VE GOTTA
KEEP WORKING.
IT MAY SEEM KIND OF
HOPELESS NOW,
BUT IF WE JUST STAY POSITIVE
AND STICK TO IT,
I KNOW IT'S BOUND TO BECOME
SOFT, RICH SOIL EVENTUALLY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, BRO.
AS LONG AS WE STAY POSITIVE,
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN'T DO.
( laughs )
- MY BROTHER AND I STRUGGLED
TO SURVIVE
AFTER LOSING BOTH OF OUR
PARENTS.  IT WAS A TRYING TIME.
WE WORKED DILIGENTLY
IN THE HOPES
OF GROWING VEGETABLES
IN OUR MEAGER GARDEN.
UNFORTUNATELY, WHEN IT CAME TIME
FOR THE HARVEST,
WE WERE LEFT DISAPPOINTED.
- ( sobs )I CAN'T BELIEVE WE DID
ALL THAT WORK FOR NOTHING, BRO.
I KNEW THIS TOPSOIL
WAS NO GOOD.
WE DIDN'T GROW
A SINGLE VEGETABLE.  THIS SUCKS!
- COME ON, DON'T CRY, WALLY.
- I CAN'T HELP IT.
- ( gasps )
- WE DID IT.  WE GREW ONE!
CHECK IT OUT.
- OH, YEAH!
- ( stomach rumbling )
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I'M READY TO CHOW DOWN.
- WE'RE NOT EATING ANYTHING
UNTIL WE'VE SAID GRACE.
A SINGLE POTATO MAY NOT
LOOK LIKE MUCH TO OTHERS,
BUT IN OUR EYES,
IT'S A BOUNTIFUL HARVEST
THAT HAS RENEWED
OUR DETERMINATION AND HOPE.
THANK YOU FOR THIS BLESSING
OF FOOD THAT YOU'VE GIVEN US.
- YEAH, THANKS A LOT
FOR THE GRUB.
NOW LET'S EAT UP.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GET HALF.
- MY STOMACH'S KIND OF BEEN
BOTHERING ME TODAY,
SO YOU CAN HAVE THE WHOLE THING.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
- WELL, MY STOMACH'S
KIND OF BEEN BOTHERING ME, TOO,
SO THERE'S NO WAY I CAN EAT
THE WHOLE THING BY MYSELF.
HELP ME OUT AND TAKE HALF,
WOULD YOU?
- THANKS.
- ( laughs )
- EVEN THOUGH MANY YEARS
HAVE PASSED SINCE THAT DAY,
I CAN STILL REMEMBER THE TASTE
OF THAT POTATO.
- I KNOW YOUR BROTHER, RICHARD.
- YOU DO?
- YES,
HE'S AN OLD FRIEND OF MINE.
HE'S HAPPILY TRAVELING
THE CONTINENT RIGHT NOW.
- ( crying )
ALL THESE YEARS
I KEPT TELLING MYSELF
THAT IF I JUST STAYED POSITIVE,
A MIRACLE WOULD HAPPEN,
AND, LO AND BEHOLD, IT HAS.
( sobbing )
THANK YOU.  THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
( continues sobbing )
- I FEEL KIND OF BAD FOR HIM,
YOU KNOW?
- ME, TOO.
- I GUESS IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
- IT MUST'VE BEEN DIFFICULT,
BUT I THINK HE MADE
THE RIGHT DECISION.
- COME ON. HELP ME OUT HERE!
IF YOU DON'T UNDO
THE ENCHANTMENT,
I'M GONNA WET MYSELF.
- YOU ARE SO DISGUSTING!
- SORRY, BUT I'M AFRAID
THAT'S SIMPLY NOT AN OPTION
AT THIS TIME.  NOT TILL WE'VE
CAPTURED OUR TRUE OBJECTIVE.
A FIEND WHO INFILTRATED
AND DESTROYED THE MAGIC COUNCIL
AND FIRED THE ETHERION CANNON.
A MAN MORE VILLAINOUS
THAN THE ORACION SEIS.
TRULY BLACK OF HEART.
I'M REFERRING TO YOU, JELLAL.
LET'S GO.
KNOW THAT IF YOU RESIST,
WE HAVE EXPLICIT ORDERS
TO KILL YOU.
- LEAVE HIM ALONE.
- YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE, MAN.
- JELLAL FERNANDES
IS A CRIMINAL.
SOCIETY IS IN DANGER
AS LONG AS HE ROAMS FREE.
HE MUST BE BROUGHT TO JUSTICE.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: NOW THAT WE'VE DEFEATED
THE ORACION SEIS,
WE CAN FINALLY
GO BACK TO THE GUILD HALL.
- Natsu: IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I THOUGHT THIS JOB WAS
GONNA DO US IN.  I MEAN, THOSE
GUYS WERE RIDICULOUSLY STRONG.
- WE GOT IN SOME PRETTY
STICKY SITUATIONS, TOO.
- NO JOKE.  IT'S A GOOD THING
WE JOINED THE ALLIANCE
'CAUSE WE COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
ON OUR OWN.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: I THINK WE DESERVE
A VICTORY PARTY
AFTER SUCH A TOUGH MISSION.
- Natsu: LET'S MAKE IT HAPPEN
WHEN WE GET BACK.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
- Both: PARTY!  PARTY!