- HEY, GUYS.
READY FOR SOME
MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
THE KINGDOM OF FIORE,
A PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
HOWEVER...
SUBMITTED FOR
YOUR APPROVAL,
A TYPE OF MAGIC THAT
IS PARTICULARLY EERIE,
A SPELL THAT MAY CAUSE
THE MINDS OF YOU,
OUR DEAR VIEWERS,
TO LEAVE YOUR BODIES
AND BE TRANSPORTED
TO THAT FARAWAY MAGICAL REALM.
DON'T PANIC.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( door opens )
- Erza: IS MASTER MAKAROV HERE?
- YOU'RE FINALLY BACK
FROM YOUR ISLAND GETAWAY.
SO HOW WAS IT?
DID YOU HAVE FUN?
- IT WAS WORK,
NOT A VACATION.
- UH, MIRAJANE, I WOULDN'T
JOKE WITH HER RIGHT NOW.
- WHERE IS MAKAROV?
- HE WENT OUT OF TOWN
FOR SOME KIND OF
LAST-MINUTE COUNCIL MEETING
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
HE'S BEEN GONE SINCE YESTERDAY.
- WHEW.
- WELL, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- YES, WE WON'T HAVE
TO DEAL WITH THAT
UNTIL GRAMPS GETS BACK.
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
I WASN'T READY TO STARE
INTO THE FACE OF DEATH.
I'VE STILL GOT
EIGHT MORE LIVES.
- I CAN'T STAND IT ANYMORE.
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY
FREAKING ME OUT.
HOW'S HE GONNA PUNISH US?
I CAN'T DIE NOW.
I'M STILL YOUNG AND I HAVE
SO MUCH TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
- ALL OF YOU, SHUT UP!
- ( gasping )
- DO YOU KNOW WHEN THE MASTER
IS PLANNING TO RETURN?
- NO, BUT I WOULD IMAGINE
HE'LL BE COMING BACK
ANY TIME NOW.
- NOW, LISTEN UP, YOU FOOLS.
YOU'RE NOT
GETTING OFF THE HOOK.
YOU BROKE GUILD RULES
BY TAKING ON
THAT S-CLASS QUEST.
PREPARE TO BE PUNISHED.
- ( boys whimper )
- HOW DO I PREPARE MYSELF
WHEN I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?!
- WELL, IT WAS
NICE KNOWING YOU.
( sighs )
IT'S A CRYING SHAME.
THOSE TWO BOYS ARE ONE THING,
BUT I CAN'T BELIEVE
LUCY'S GETTING PUNISHED TOO.
OH, YOU POOR GIRL.
- "YOU POOR GIRL"?
- WHAT'S THE DEAL, MAN?
HOW COME YOU DON'T
FEEL SORRY FOR US? HUH?
- WHY'RE YOU LUMPING ME
IN WITH THIS LOSER?
- ( fighting grunts )
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- IT MEANS I DON'T
EVEN WANT TO BE
IN THE SAME SENTENCE AS YOU.
DO I HAVE TO DRAW YOU A PICTURE?
- A BIG PART OF BEING A MAN
IS OWNING UP TO YOUR ACTIONS.
YOU HEAR THAT, YOU TWO?
IT'S HIGH TIME
FOR YOU TO MAN UP.
- IT'S NOT FAIR.
I'M THE CUTEST ONE HERE.
SO HOW COME NOBODY
FEELS SORRY FOR ME?
- WOULD SOMEBODY PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO US?!
- Natsu: THAT'S ONE
CREEPY-LOOKING JOB REQUEST.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- YOU GUYS ARE BACK. WHAT'S UP?
-  NOT MUCH, MAN.
WHAT THE HECK?
I CAN'T EVEN READ IT.
- READ WHAT?
- WHOA! YOU'RE BACK TOO, LUCY?
- GEEZ, IT'S REAL NICE
TO SEE YOU TOO.
WHAT IS YOUR
PROBLEM WITH ME?
- I, UH-- NOTHING.
- NO WAY!
YOU WILL NOT BE
TAKING ANY REQUESTS.
- REAL SMOOTH.
- DO THEY HAVE
TO BE SO NOISY?
- WHO CARES?
THEY ARE LIKE THE COOLEST.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME, RIGHT?
- "DECIPHER THIS TEXT
AND I'LL SEE THAT YOU'LL
INCREASE YOUR WEALTH
BY 500 THOUSAND JEWEL."
THIS ONE SOUNDS
LIKE A WINNER TO ME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- SURE DOES.
- SO IT'S A TRANSLATION JOB?
THAT'S A WEIRD REQUEST
FOR A GUILD.
WAIT, THAT'S SOME KIND
OF CRAZY ANCIENT STUFF.
NO ONE'S GONNA
BE ABLE TO READ THAT.
- Happy: HOLD ON, IT'S WRITTEN
IN MODERN LETTERS TOO.
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
NO JOBS.
- OH, YEAH, I CAN
TOTALLY READ THAT.
LET'S SEE, "UGO DERU
RASUCHI BORO KANIA."
WHAT THE-- THAT'S CRAZY.
- ( gasping )
- Macao: WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THAT'S JUST SAD.
THOSE KIDS ARE SO SCARED
OF THE MASTER'S PUNISHMENT,
THEY'RE ACTUALLY
SWEATING RAINBOWS.
- THAT'S ENOUGH BOOZE FOR YOU.
- All: UH...
- ( shivers )
SO COLD!
- WHAT?  ICE WIZARDS
DON'T GET COLD,
YOU BIG CRYBABY.
- ( shivers ) I'M SERIOUS,
YOU GUYS.
COULD SOMEBODY TURN UP
THE HEAT BEFORE
I FREEZE TO DEATH IN HERE,
PRETTY PLEASE?
- HUH?
- ( deep pitched )
WHAT THE--
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MY CHEST FEELS REALLY WEIRD
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
LIKE IT'S HEAVY.
MY BACK'S KILLING ME.
- HEY, ARE YOU FEELING
ALL RIGHT, LUCY?
- YOUR VOICE SEEMS
AWFULLY LOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I-- WHAT THE--
THAT'S WEIRD.
I DON'T REMEMBER
LYING DOWN ON
THE FLOOR LIKE THAT.
- HOLD ON.  I THOUGHT I WAS
THE ONE WHO WAS ON THE FLOOR.
( screams )
- WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU CAN'T FACE ME,
DRAGON BREATH?
WHY DO I SOUND LIKE A GIRL?
- I'M NO DOCTOR,
BUT I'D SAY IT'S PROBABLY
'CAUSE YOU ARE A GIRL.
- WHY IS EVERYONE
BEHAVING SO FOOLISHLY?
- OH, WOW, NATSU.
CHECK IT OUT.
WHERE DID HE GO?
- I'M STANDING RIGHT HERE.
WHY IS THIS PLACE SO DARK?
- I COULD BE WRONG,
BUT I REALLY DON'T THINK
I'VE ALWAYS HAD THESE.
HAVE I? HAVE I?
- WHOA!
- OH, WHY YOU!
- ( thunk )
- HEY, AND I GOT
COOL ARMOR TOO.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO ME.
I'VE NEVER FELT SO
TINY AND WEAK BEFORE.
IT'S LIKE I'VE SOMEHOW
REQUIPPED INTO A CAT.
- WHY DO THEY HAVE TO RUIN
MY QUALITY DRINKING TIME?
- THEY'RE SO COOL,
THEY COULDN'T RUIN ANYTHING.
- KINDA THEIR THING.
- ( gasping )
- Gray: OKAY, I'M STARTING
TO GET REALLY FREAKED OUT.
FIRST, I'M TOTALLY FREEZING.
AND NOW, THERE'S SOME SORT OF
CREEPY LOOK-ALIKE OF ME.
- Lucy:
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- HOW CAN YOU BE
SUCH AN IDIOT?
DON'T YOU REALIZE
WHAT HAS HAPPENED TO US?
WE'VE ALL SWITCHED BODIES.
- WHAT?
- STOP FOOLING AROUND, HAPPY.
- I'M ERZA, YOU DIMWIT.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA
YELL AT ME, LOKE,
DO IT TO MY FACE.
- SILENCE.
- YOU MEAN...
- Happy: YES, NATSU AND LOKE.
GRAY AND LUCY.
AND WORST OF ALL,
HAPPY AND I.
WE HAVE ALL SWITCHED BODIES.
- All: HUH?
- WHY SWITCHING WITH ME
THE WORST OF ALL?
- THE ANCIENT UNPELA SPELL
HAS BEEN CAST.
YOU KIDS AREN'T FEELING
LIKE YOURSELVES TODAY, HUH?
- MASTER, YOU'RE BACK.
- GRAMPS.
- I HAD NOTICED THAT
REQUEST ON THE BOARD.
BY READING WHAT WAS WRITTEN
ON THAT PAGE ALOUD,
YOU'VE CAST A POWERFUL SPELL
OF PERSONALITY TRANSFERENCE.
AND THAT SPELL IS CALLED
THE CHANGELING.
- THAT SOUNDS SCARY.
- SO YOU'RE REALLY NATSU, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- YOU IDIOT!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO US?
- ME?  ALL I DID WAS TRY
TO READ THE STUPID JOB REQUEST!
WOULD SOMEONE PLEASE
TURN ON THE LIGHTS?  COME ON.
- Makarov: THAT'S ENOUGH, LUCY--
UH, GRAY. FOR WIZARDS,
THIS SPELL SWITCH IS MORE
THAN JUST YOUR BODIES.
IT SWITCHES MAGIC AS WELL.
- WHAT?!
- ( pants )
OH, MAN, IT KIND OF FEELS LIKE
SOMEBODY JUST POURED
LAVA DOWN MY THROAT.
HEY, IS IT HOT OUT HERE
OR IS IT JUST YOU?
- ( screams )
- HUH?
( screams )
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?!
- THERE'S ONE THING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
IF THE CHANGELING SPELL
IS NOT UNDONE
WITHIN 30 MINUTES FROM THE TIME
WHEN IT WAS INITIALLY CAST,
YOU WILL NEVER RETURN
TO THE WAY YOU WERE BEFORE.
OR SO SAYS THE LEGEND
AT LEAST.
- WHAT?!
- DO YOU KNOW
HOW MANY MINUTES
WE'VE BEEN MIXED UP FOR?
- 16.
SO YOU HAVE 14 LEFT.
- GRAMPS, ISN'T THERE A WAY
TO LIFT THE SPELL
AND CHANGE US BACK?
- HMM.
SINCE THIS IS SUCH
AN ANCIENT MAGIC,
IT WOULD ONLY STAND TO REASON
THAT I... DON'T KNOW.
- OH NO.
- I MUST SAY I'M DISAPPOINTED.
I WAS SO LOOKING FORWARD
TO PUNISHING YOU.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
YOUR HANDS FULL FOR NOW.
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU KIDS.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT DOES IT.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
- NO!  GET AHOLD OF YOURSELF.
- LET GO!
- SO, EVEN THOUGH
GRAY'S IN LUCY'S BODY,
HE STILL LIKES TO TAKE OFF
HIS CLOTHES.
- THEN THAT MEANS--
- THAT MEANS WHAT?
- THIS'LL BE AWESOME.
- NO, HAPPY!
- OKAY, HERE I GO.
- HAPPY!
STOP THIS AT ONCE!
- REQUIP!
CHECK ME OUT, YOU GUYS.
YAY!
UPPA!
TA-DA.
- WHOA, ERZA LOOKS SMOKIN' HOT!
- HOW DARE YOU!
NO, THIS CAN'T BE.
I WAS AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
AND NOW I'M SO WEAK.
- MAN, I WAS TRYING
TO CHANGE INTO
ONE OF THOSE COOL
SUITS OF ARMOR SHE HAS..
- I SEE, WE SWITCHED OUR MAGIC
WITH EACH OTHER,
BUT EVERYONE
TOTALLY STINKS AT IT.
- HEY, LOKE--
OR WHOEVER'S INSIDE HIM.
- GEEZ, IT'S ME, NATSU, OKAY?
- HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT
WHAT MAGIC HE USES?
- YEAH, COME ON.
BE A MAN, KID.  SHOW US.
- I DON'T KNOW.  I DON'T FEEL
ANYTHING HAPPENING MAGIC-WISE.
EVERYTHING JUST
KIND OF SEEMS FUZZY.
( groans ) I DON'T THINK I CAN
TAKE THIS PRESSURE ANYMORE.
- HEY, GUYS, YOU GOT TO HELP ME!
- WHAT'S WITH THAT FIRE?
- IT'S LIKE HE'S DROOLING.
- WELL, THAT'S CERTAINLY
NOT THREATENING.
- I MUST ADMIT,
FLYING IS WAY MORE FUN
THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
I SHOULDN'T BE WASTING
MY PRECIOUS TIME LIKE THIS.
I NEED TO BE
CHANGED BACK AT ONCE.
- WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- HEY, GRAY OR, UH, LUCY,
YOU'RE DROPPING ICE, HON.
- I HATE THIS.
WHY ME?
- Levy:
NO NEED TO WORRY, LUCY.
- LEVY, IT'S YOU.
- LEVY?
- THE SHADOW GEAR TEAM
IS HERE TO SAVE THE DAY.
YOU GUYS WILL BE BACK
TO NORMAL IN NO TIME.
- OH YEAH, WE GOT THIS.
NO SWEAT.
- NOW, DO YOUR THING, LEVY.
- WHEN YOU BOYS SAY "WE,"
YOU REALLY MEAN "HER," RIGHT?
- ( laughing )
- YOU'RE SO SWEET TO HELP US.
- ANYTHING FOR MY GIRL.
BESIDES, I WANT TO
READ YOUR NOVEL.
AND IT'D BE KIND OF WEIRD
TALKING ABOUT IT WITH GRAY.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- WELL, I DO KNOW A THING OR TWO
ABOUT ANCIENT TEXTS.
I'LL START BY TAKING A LOOK
AT WHAT WAS WRITTEN
ON THE FLYER ITSELF.
- SOUNDS GOOD, BUT DO IT QUICK.
- LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
WE NEED TO LET LEVY
WORK IN PEACE.
WHY DID I HAVE
A FISH IN MY MOUTH?
- 'CAUSE THEY'RE YUMMY.
- OKAY.
"UGO DERU..."
- PLEASE HURRY.
THERE'S ONLY 10 MINUTES LEFT.
- HEY, YOU SURE IT'S SAFE
TO READ THE WORDS
OUT LOUD LIKE THAT?
- DON'T WORRY.
IT'S TOTALLY SAFE
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T READ
EVERYTHING IN THE CORRECT ORDER.
NOW...
- THERE'S NOT MUCH TIME!
UGH, I CAN'T TAKE IT!
I FEEL SO WEIRD.
CHANGE ME BACK.
- AWW, I DON'T THINK
IT'S ALL THAT BAD.
ONE MORE TIME!
RE--
- I SWEAR YOU'LL
LOSE A LIFE, CAT!
- SO HOW'S IT GOING, LEVY?
- HAVE YOU FIGURED IT OUT?
- NO, I'M STUMPED.
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
- OH NO, I NEVER
THOUGHT MY FATE
WOULD BE TO
LIVE OUT MY DAYS
AS SOME STRANGE FLYING CAT.
- WHAT'S SO TERRIBLE
ABOUT THAT, HUH?
- NO!
- OOH!
- I TOLD YOU
NOT TO DO THAT!
- UH, I FEEL SO FUNKY.
- THE GIRLS ARE NEVER
GONNA TALK TO ME NOW.
- I WANT TO SWITCH
WITH SOMEONE.
- NOT WITH ME, KIDDO.
I'D DIE IF I WAS UNDERAGE.
- LOOK, I KNOW YOU GUYS
ARE FREAKING OUT,
BUT I'M STILL
WORKING ON IT, OKAY?
- HOW MUCH TIME
DO WE HAVE?
- ABOUT EIGHT MINUTES.
HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT YOU MIGHT START PREPARING
FOR THE WORST.
- OH NO.
- ( whistle blows )
- ( drum thumping )
- Both: GO, GO!
GO, LEVY!
- THOSE TWO GUYS ARE JUST HER
PERSONAL CHEERLEADERS?
- SO "DERU" IS...
OH, I SEE.
THAT MUST MEAN...
- ( all sigh )
- SO WHAT HAPPENS IF WE END UP
GETTING STUCK LIKE THIS?
- HUH?  WHAT DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- ARE WE JUST GONNA TRY
TO ADJUST TO OUR NEW BODIES
AND GO BACK TO WORK?
- WELL, YEAH,
I GUESS WE'D HAVE TO.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF OPTIONS.
- WHATEVER HAPPENS
IS TOTALLY FINE WITH ME.
IF I STAY QUIET,
EVERYONE'LL BE NICE TO ME
BECAUSE I'M SCARY NOW.
- WHAT?
- WELL, NO ONE ASKED FOR
YOUR OPINION, DID THEY?
STUPID CAT.
I JUST WANT TO BE
A CUTE GIRL AGAIN.
- ( both sigh )
- ARE THOSE FROZEN
CHUNKS OF DROOL?
THAT IS SO GROSS, MAN.
- I'M NOT A MAN!
AND I KNOW IT'S GROSS.
YOU THINK I'M DOING
THIS ON PURPOSE?
UH...
- WHAT IS IT, GRAY?
ER, I MEAN LUCY.
- I JUST REALIZED SOMETHING.
IF WE GET STUCK
LIKE THIS FOREVER
AND NONE OF US HAVE A CLUE
HOW TO USE OUR MAGIC ANYMORE,
IF WE DID TAKE A JOB,
WE'D NEVER BE ABLE TO FINISH IT.
- AWW, GEEZ, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- WE STINK.
- AND THAT MEANS...
- All: WE'RE THE WEAKEST TEAM
IN FAIRY TAIL NOW.
- LET'S DO THIS, HAPPY.
- AYE.
- ICE MAKE: SOMETHING OR OTHER.
- UH, HOLD ON.
STUPID KEYS.
- OH, WOW, BEING ABLE TO FLY
IS SO FUN.
- ( all groan )
- NO!
WHAT'S THE POINT OF LIVING
IF I CAN'T EVEN
BURN STUFF ANYMORE?
- I AM AN S-CLASS WIZARD
AND I REFUSE TO BE PART
OF THE WEAKEST TEAM
IN THE ENTIRE GUILD.
IF ONLY I WASN'T TRAPPED
IN THIS FORM...
- YOU'RE MEAN.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU'RE COMPLAINING SO MUCH.
I LIKE BEING A CAT.
- ( groans )
- JUST WHAT WERE YOU TRYING
TO DO THERE, ERZA?
ER, I MEAN, HAPPY?
- EVER SINCE WE'VE SWITCHED,
SHE'S BEEN SAYING MEAN STUFF.
SO I GOT MAD AND
TRIED TO FLY AWAY.
BUT I COULDN'T FLY AWAY
'CAUSE I DON'T
HAVE MY WINGS ANYMORE.
- I'M SORRY I WAS MEAN.
I PROMISE I'LL BE--
- YES, THAT'S IT.
- ( gasps )
- REALLY?
SO YOU CAN LIFT THE SPELL?
- COME ON.  DO IT.
- THIS IS WHAT IT SAYS.
"MAY THIS ETERNAL EXCHANGE
PROVIDE YOU WITH
ETERNAL HAPPINESS."
KIND OF CUTE, ISN'T IT?
- AW, YEAH, IT IS.
- "MAY THIS ETERNAL EXCHANGE
PROVIDE YOU WITH
ETERNAL HAPPINESS."  HUH.
- YEAH, AND...
- IN OTHER WORDS, EVERYBODY
WHO'S BEEN SWITCHED
BY THE SPELL
WILL LIVE HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
YOU'RE SO LUCKY.
I'M SO GLAD
I FIGURED IT OUT.
- OH, NO WAY!
ARE YOU TELLING ME
WE'RE STUCK
LIKE THIS FOREVER?!
- WE WANTED YOU TO LIFT
THE SPELL,
NOT READ IT.
REMEMBER?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
- YOU'VE GOT THIS.
I HAVE FAITH THAT YOU CAN DO IT.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO WORK
A LITTLE FASTER, OKAY?
MAYBE THERE'S SOME KIND OF CODE
OR HIDDEN MESSAGE
IN THE WORDS,
YOU KNOW,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
- GO, GO!  GO, LEVY!
- ISN'T ALL THAT RACKET
GONNA DISTRACT HER?
- NO, THEY'RE JUST TRYING
TO GET HER PUMPED UP.
AND THEY NEED
ALL THE HELP THEY CAN GET.
- HUH?
- GO, GO!  GO LEVY!
( cheering )
- I'M STILL NOT SEEING ANY
KIND OF A PATTERN HERE.
IT DOESN'T SEEM
TO MAKE ANY SENSE.
- ( groans )
- THREE MINUTES LEFT.
- THREE MINUTES?!
- WELL, THIS IS IT.
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
FISH FOR BREAKFAST,
LUNCH, AND DINNER.
I'VE WORKED SO HARD.
AND NOW I'M GOING
TO SPEND MY DAYS
CHASING MICE AND
LITTLE PIECES OF STRING.
- NO, WAIT! COME BACK
HERE, HAPPY. I MEAN, ERZA!
- SORRY I GOT UPSET.
I KNOW THIS IS HARD
FOR BOTH OF US.
- REALLY?
YOU DO?
- NOW'S NOT THE TIME FOR US
TO BE ARGUING LIKE THIS.
WILL YOU PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- YES, OF COURSE.
I HOPE YOU'LL
FORGIVE ME TOO.
- AYE, HERE'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
- A FISH, I--
DON'T WANT IT!
- COULD YOU BE ANY
MORE CLUELESS?
- HAVE YOU
FIGURED IT OUT YET?
- THE SITUATION IS DIRE
WITH JUST ONE MINUTE TO GO.
- I DON'T RECALL ASKING
YOU FOR THE TIME,
SO SHUT YOUR TRAP, 'KAY?!
- GEEZ, I WAS JUST
TRYING TO HELP.
- OKAY, I THINK
I'VE ALMOST GOT
THIS LAST PART OF IT
WORKED OUT.
- WORK IT, LEVY.  YEAH!
YOU'RE ON FIRE!
- HE'S TOO GOOD AT THAT.
- STILL TRYING TO BREAK
THE SPELL, ARE YOU?
- LOOK, IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO TEACH US A LESSON HERE,
WE'VE LEARNED IT ALREADY, OKAY?
- OH.
- ( gasps )
- YES, MASTER?
- NOPE.  NEVER MIND, KIDS.
I'M DRAWING A BLANK.
- ( all groan )
- OH! WE'RE NOT
GONNA MAKE IT!
- TAKING MY SHIRT OFF
ISN'T GONNA
CHANGE ANYTHING, GRAY!
- LET GO OF ME!
- YOU GUYS HAVE ABOUT
40 SECONDS LEFT,
MORE OR LESS,
STARTING NOW.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "MORE OR LESS"?!
- I JUST REMEMBERED SOMETHING
ABOUT THE SPELL.
- WHAT IS IT?
- WHILE IT CAN BE LIFTED,
I'M AFRAID THAT IT HAS
TO BE DONE ONE PAIR AT A TIME.
MEANING IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO
CHANGE ALL OF YOU BACK AT ONCE.
- WHAT?
- 30 SECONDS-ISH.
- WHICH PAIR'S GOING FIRST?
- IT SHOULD BE ME
AND OTHER ME.
DON'T YOU THINK?
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- THAT IS SO NOT FAIR.
I THINK IT SHOULD
BE ME AND GRAY.
- HOLD ON, AS FAIRY TAIL'S
STRONGEST FEMALE WIZARD,
I SHOULD GO FIRST.
IT'S FOR THE GOOD OF THE GUILD.
- WELL, I DON'T CARE
EITHER WAY.
- ( arguing )
- THIS IS GETTING UGLY.
- AT LEAST THEY CAN'T USE
THEIR MAGIC AGAINST EACH OTHER.
-  JUST 15 SECONDS LEFT.
- HOLD ON, YOU GUYS,
I GOT IT.
- AND 12, 11...
- SERIOUSLY?
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL TRY TO EXPLAIN
THIS TO YOU REALLY QUICK.
- AND NINE, EIGHT...
- ( thuds )
- ( groans )
- NO TIME.
JUST CHANGE US BACK.
HURRY!
- YEAH, RIGHT.
OKAY, HERE GOES.
"AINAK OROB
IHCUSAR URED OGU!
AINAK OROB
IHCUSAR URED OGU!"
- ( sighs )
- HEY, I'M BACK TO NORMAL, GUYS.
- ME TOO.
MAN, THAT WAS CLOSE.
- SO NOW YOU'RE DROOLING
ICE CUBES ON PURPOSE?
- YOU'RE AWESOME, LEVY.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- OH, YEAH.
- OUR CHEERING WORKED, HUH?
- YOU GOT TO TELL US--
HOW'D YOU DO IT?
WHEN I REALIZED THE WORDS
THEMSELVES HAD NO MEANING,
I DECIDED TO READ
THEM BACKWARDS.
IT'S ACTUALLY AN OLD TRICK.
ANCIENT LANGUAGES LIKE THIS
USUALLY DIDN'T HAVE
THAT MANY LETTERS.
SO SOMETIMES THEY HAD TO BE
A LITTLE BIT MORE CREATIVE
WITH HOW THEY USED THEIR WORDS.
THAT'S WHY,
WHEN I REVERSED THE WORDS,
IT REVERSED THE SPELL TOO.
- HOW COOL. I NEVER WOULD
HAVE THOUGHT OF THAT.
- WE OWE YOU BIG TIME, LEVY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I'M STILL
IN THE WRONG BODY!
- WHAT?
- ME TOO.
I'M STILL A STUPID CAT.
- WOW, YOU MEAN I GET
TO STAY LIKE THIS?
- ( screams )
- WELL, THAT DOES IT
FOR TIME.
YOU DID GET ONE PAIR
SWITCHED BACK.
SO I GUESS THAT'S
SOMETHING TO BE PROUD OF.
- NO, THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
SOME KIND OF MIX UP.
PLEASE, LEVY,
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING ELSE YOU CAN TRY.
- SORRY, MAYBE I DIDN'T
PRONOUNCE IT RIGHT.
- All: WHAT?!
- SO THAT'S IT?
WE'RE STUCK
LIKE THIS FOREVER.
- I CAN'T SPEND
THE REST OF MY LIFE
AS SOME PINK-HAIRED FIRE
DROOLING FREAK OF NATURE.
- WAKE UP, ERZA.
THIS IS ALL SOME
HORRIBLE NIGHTMARE
AND YOU NEED TO WAKE UP.
- OH, COME ON, RELAX.
IT'S NOT ALL THAT BAD.
- Mirajane: NOW, NOW,
DON'T LOSE HEART.
THERE'S GOT TO
BE ANOTHER WAY.
HUH?
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
HEY, GUYS, DID I GET SHORTER?
- OH NO!  MIRAJANE?!
- DON'T TELL ME THAT MIRA
SWITCHED BODIES WITH GRAMPS.
- WHOO BOY!  YOU WON'T HEAR ME
COMPLAINING ABOUT THAT!
- NO!  THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
- WHO ELSE?
- ALL OF YOU NEED TO JUST
MAN UP AND GET OVER IT, OKAY?
WHAT'S THE DEAL? WHY DO I SMELL
LIKE A BREWERY ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- WHAT?  HEY, HOW DID--
OH MAN, I REALLY THINK
I MIGHT NEED TO TAKE
A BIT OF A NAP RIGHT NOW.
- HEY, UH, DROY?  HMM?!
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT NOW, JET?
- HEY, MAN, STOP
LOOKING LIKE ME!
- I DON'T THINK ANYBODY'S
GONNA BE ABLE
TO TELL THE DIFFERENCE
WITH YOU TWO.
BUT IN MY CASE,
HAVING A BODY LIKE THIS
IS A DREAM COME TRUE.
- HE'S CREEPING ME OUT, LEVY!
PLEASE HELP ME.
- ( overlapping chatter )
- UH...
- SORRY, BUT I THINK I'M IN
WAY OVER MY HEAD HERE.
- THIS IS AWESOME.
EVERYONE'S SOMEONE ELSE NOW.
- HAVE YOU GONE
COMPLETELY NUTS?
THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- Narrator:
MAGIC IS NOT A TOY.
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE,
IT CAN TURN YOUR WORLD
ON ITS HEAD.
THE VERY FABRIC OF YOUR BEING
CAN BE PULLED FROM YOU
IN AN INSTANT.
SO DON'T TAKE IT LIGHTLY.
- ( theme music plays )
- Narrator:
UNTIL NEXT TIME...
- PLEASE TURN US BACK!
- YOU'RE SERIOUSLY
JUST GONNA END IT?
- AYE.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: PROFESSOR HAPPY'S CLASS
ABOUT FAIRY TAIL.
TODAY WE'RE GONNA LEARN
HOW TO GET A JOB
IN THIS EXCITING GUILD.
SO LISTEN UP.
WHEN SOMEONE NEEDS HELP
FROM A WIZARD,
A JOB IS POSTED ON
THE GUILD'S REQUEST BOARD.
THERE, WIZARDS CAN PICK ANY JOB
THEY WANT TO MAKE MONEY.
IT HELPS IF YOU'VE GOT
A FRIEND TO GO ALONG WITH YOU.
YOU CAN EVEN COME UP
WITH A COOL TEAM NAME.
YAY!  THAT'S TODAY'S CLASS.
DISMISSED.
- ( chairs scrape )
- AYE!
- Natsu: SORRY, BUDDY.
BUT I DON'T THINK ERZA
LIKED BEING YOU ALL THAT MUCH.
- SHE WAS PROBABLY JUST MAD
'CAUSE SHE COULDN'T
FIGURE OUT HOW TO FLY.
- YEAH, KIND OF REMINDED ME
OF THE DAY YOU WERE BORN.
- AYE, I DON'T MEAN TO BRAG,
BUT SINCE IT WAS REALLY ERZA
PRETENDING TO BE ME,
SHE COULDN'T EVEN COME CLOSE
TO BEING AS CUTE AS I AM.
- Natsu:
HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU.
BUT YOU WERE KIND
OF GROSS-LOOKING
WHEN YOU WERE BORN.
- NO WAY.
EVERYBODY TOLD ME
I WAS CUTE.
- WELL, YOU WERE,
BUT IN A GROSS KIND OF WAY.