- HEY, GUYS. READY FOR
SOME MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS
ON IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO
CLOSE TO THE TV.
- ( birds caw )
- ( laughing )
- OWEE, OWEE, OWEE. HOT,
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT.
- HUP.
- ON IT. HAHA!
- LET ME OFF THIS THING.
- THIS WAS YOUR IDEA
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- ( laughing )
- Narrator: AKANE RESORT.
FIORE'S MOST POPULAR
VACATION SPOT,
WHERE IT'S CITIZENS CAN
RELAX AND ENJOY THEMSELVES
IN A NUMBER OF WAYS.
BOTH IT'S AMUSEMENT PARK
AND THE ADJOINING HOTEL
ARE RATED FIRST CLASS.
ONE VISIT TO IT'S WHITE SAND
BEACH WILL MAKE YOU WANT
TO COME BACK AGAIN AND AGAIN.
ALL THIS OVERLOOKS
THE OCEAN WATER, SPARKLING
AS FAR AS THE EYE CAN SEE.
USING THE TICKETS LOKE
GAVE THEM FOR THEIR HELP,
NATSU, LUCY, AND THE OTHERS
ENJOY SOME WELL-DESERVED
FUN IN THE SUN.
- GIVE ME BACK MY BATHING SUIT.
- NO WAY, MAN.
- ( laughing )
I DON'T THINK HAPPY LIKES
BEING USED AS A COVER UP.
- MY BELOVED, GRAY.
WHAT A HUNK.
- Happy: THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
- I REALLY HAD
A GREAT TIME TODAY.
( sighs )
IT WAS WONDERFUL.
- Jellal: DON'T YOU SEE? THERE'S
NO FREEDOM IN THIS WORLD.
- ( gasps )
( breathing heavily )
JUST A DREAM.
I MUST'VE FALLEN ASLEEP
WITHOUT REALIZING IT.
- ( birds cawing )
- I ALWAYS FEEL MORE
AT EASE WEARING ARMOR.
ALTHOUGH, AS A WARDROBE CHOICE,
I GUESS IT'S NOT
THE MOST FEMININE.
- ( knocking on door )
- ERZA. GET OUT OF THE ROOM
AND COME HAVE SOME FUN.
NATSU AND GRAY
ARE DOWNSTAIRS.
WANT TO GO FIND THEM
AND PLAY SOME GAMES?
- THAT'S RIGHT, THERE'S A
CASINO HERE, ISN'T THERE?
IN THAT CASE.
- Lucy: WOW.
- SO, HOW DO I LOOK?
- UH, YOU LOOK GREAT.
MAYBE A LITTLE ON THE
GLITZY SIDE BUT WHATEVER.
- COME ON,
COME ON. LET'S GO.
- I GUESS IT'S OKAY TO RELAX
AND ENJOY MYSELF EVERY
ONCE IN A WHILE, ISN'T IT?
- ( people chattering )
- ( cheering )
- ( screaming )
- SEVENTEEN, COME ON.
- DON'T BE MEAN, SEVENTEEN.
- Natsu: WHOA.
- Happy: YOU GOT IT.
- ( machine buzzes )
- ( both screaming )
- HEY, WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
- CURSE YOU, SEVENTEEN.
- UH SIR, PLEASE DON'T
HIT THE MACHINE.
- BUT IT ACTED LIKE IT WAS
GOING TO GIVE ME MY NUMBER.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
- NO FAIR.
- ( Natsu crying )
- CRYING WON'T HELP, SIR.
- GIVE US A SEVENTEEN RIGHT
NOW THAT MACHINE IS A LIAR.
- MAN, THEY ARE SUCH
SORE LOSERS.
- GRAY, MY DARLING.
I'M JUVIA. DO YOU REMEMBER ME?
- YEAH, YOU'RE THAT
CHICK FROM PHANTOM.
- COME BACK SEVENTEEN.
I'LL DO ANYTHING.
- SIR, PLEASE DON'T DO THAT.
- Wally: COOL YOUR JETS, BOY.
EITHER PLAY NICE LIKE
THE REST OF THE GROWN UPS
OR HIT THE BRICKS, YOU GET ME?
- SQUARE?
- BLOCKHEAD?
- NOW, I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
SOME FRIENDLY ADVICE, PAL.
IN LIFE, YOU GOT ONE
OF TWO PATHS TO TAKE.
- HUH?
- ( screams )
- WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
- NATSU.
- YOU CAN EITHER
LIVE A DANDY LIFE...
...OR DIE A JEALOUS POSER, SEE?
- Gray: I HEARD PHANTOM
WAS DISBANDED.
THAT HAD TO BE TOUGH ON YOU.
- YES, BUT NOW I'M A FREE WIZARD
AND I CAN JOIN ANY GUILD I WANT.
- I SEE AND I TAKE
IT YOU'RE WANTING
TO BE A MEMBER OF
FAIRY TAIL, HUH?
- OH, YES. VERY MUCH SO.
- I DON'T KNOW, AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT JUST WENT DOWN,
I MEAN, I PERSONALLY DON'T MIND,
BUT WHO KNOWS WHAT
THE MASTER'LL SAY.
- I PROMISE, I'LL DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES!
- IF I WERE YOU, I'D BE CAREFUL
ABOUT MAKING PROMISES LIKE THAT.
- GRAY FULLBUSTER.
- ( people screaming )
- WHAT'S ALL THE
COMMOTION ABOUT?
- IT SOUNDS LIKE THE PARADE
HAS STARTED OUTSIDE.
- Lucy: MAKES SENSE.
- Erza: YEAH.
- JUVIA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, BUDDY?
- WHERE IS ERZA?
- COME ON, SING.
- ERZA?
- OH, WOW, CHECK IT OUT.
YOU TOTALLY GOT A STRAIGHT.
- LOOKS LIKE TODAY
IS MY LUCKY DAY.
- DEALER CHANGE.
- RIGHT.
- I HAVE A FEELING THAT THIS HOT
STREAK IS JUST GETTING STARTED.
- OH, YEAH?
- IN THAT CASE,
I'VE GOT A SPECIAL GAME
FOR YOU FOLKS TONIGHT.
AND WHILE WE'RE AT IT,
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE RAISE THE STAKES
A BIT HIGHER, SISTER?
- IT CAN'T BE. SHO?
IS THAT YOU?
- SO, YOU DO REMEMBER ME.
- YOU KNOW HIM?
- YOU'RE... YOU'RE ALIVE?
- ALIVE?
- UH, I MEAN...
- Lucy: YOU OKAY?
- NOW, WHERE IS SHE?
- YOU THINK I'D TELL YOU, HUH?
- I WON'T ALLOW YOU TO SO MUCH
AS LAY A FINGER ON MY BELOVED.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO
THROUGH ME FIRST.
- JUVIA.
- ERZA NEEDS YOUR HELP.
I FEAR SHE IS IN GRAVE DANGER.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- AH, YOU'VE LOCATED HER.
YES, I SEE. SO, I SHOULD CLEAN
THINGS UP HERE? UNDERSTOOD.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO THE LIGHTS?
- IT'S MAGIC OF THE DARK
LINEAGE. DARK MOMENT.
- HEY, WHAT GIVES?
WHO TURNED OUT THE LIGHTS?
- Happy: I CAN'T SEE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
- I'M RIGHT HERE,
WHEREVER THAT IS.
- GOOD NIGHT, BOY.
- UH-UH, NO WAY.
- ( gunshot )
- NATSU.
- A GUNSHOT?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WHERE'D HE GO?
- I'M RIGHT HERE, SISTER.
- ( people clamoring )
- OH, NO.
- HE TRAPPED THEM
INSIDE THE CARDS?
- HELP PLEASE.
- COOL, HUH?
- YOU USE MAGIC?
- THAT'S RIGHT. YOU'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONE WITH POWERS ANYMORE.
- BUT WHO TAUGHT YOU THAT?
- MEOW.
- LET HER GO.
- WELL, AREN'T YOU ALL ROSY?
- MILLIANNA? YOU CAN
USE MAGIC, TOO?
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE, ERZY-WERZY.
- PLEASE, YOU HAVE
TO LET HER GO.
SHE'S OKAY,
SHE'S A FRIEND OF MINE.
- MEOW. A FRIEND, HUH?
- WE USED TO BE FRIENDS
OF YOURS, TOO.
REMEMBER? GOOD FRIENDS.
- THESE CREEPS
WERE HER FRIENDS?
- UH, I DO.
- WE WERE VERY CLOSE.
AT LEAST, WE WERE,
UNTIL YOU DECIDED TO BETRAY US.
- WHY DON'T YOU CUT
THE DAME A LITTLE SLACK, PAL?
- KEEP THOSE
EMOTIONS IN CHECK
AND EVERYTHING WILL
BE REAL DANDY.
- WHAT? A BLOCKHEAD.
- VERY NICE. LIFE ON THE
OUTSIDE'S BEEN GOOD TO YOU,
HUH, DOLL?
- WAIT A MINUTE, WALLY?
- I'VE GONE THROUGH
SOME CHANGES MYSELF.
OLD MAD DOG
WALLY YOU GREW UP
WITH HAS SEEN A LOT
SINCE THE OLD DAYS.
YOU SEE, I'M MUCH
SMOOTHER NOW.
- YOU PRACTICE MAGIC AS WELL?
- WHY ARE YOU SO SURPRISED?
IT'S NOT THAT HARD ONCE
YOU GET THE HANG OF IT.
OF COURSE, YOU ALREADY
KNEW THAT, DIDN'T YOU?
- SIMON.
-( screams )
- ERZA, WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
WHY IS HE CALLING YOU SISTER?
- ( sighs )
HE'S NOT ACTUALLY MY BROTHER.
BUT WE ALL GREW UP TOGETHER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU
JOINED FAIRY TAIL
WHEN YOU WERE JUST
A LITTLE GIRL.
- THIS WAS BEFORE
I JOINED THE GUILD.
WHY DID YOU FIND ME?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
- WE'RE HERE TO TAKE
YOU BACK WITH US.
- I'M BEGGING YOU.
PLEASE RELEASE LUCY.
- WHO CARES ABOUT HER?
WE WANT YOU, SISTER.
- LISTEN BIM. DON'T MAKE
THIS GET UGLY.
- NO, DON'T HURT HER.
NO. PLEASE, WALLY.
- ( screams )
- ERZA. SOMEBODY HELP.
- WE GOT WHAT WE CAME
FOR. LET'S GO HOME.
- SURE SHE'S OKAY?
- SHE'S JUST TAKING A NAP.
- Lucy: HOLD IT.
JUST WHERE DO YOU JERKS
THINK YOU'RE TAKING HER?
I HOPE YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO GET AWAY WITH THIS.
NATSU AND GRAY ARE GOING
TO FIND YOU AND WHEN THEY DO,
THEY'RE GOING TO MAKE YOU PAY.
- SORRY TOOTS, BUT THOSE GINKS
GOING TO BE LICKING PAVEMENT
FOR A WHILE, YOU GET ME?
- WHAT?
- THOSE TWO WERE
NOTHING BUT TALK.
- Lucy: BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU MEAN THEY'RE...
- Wally: YEAH, SLEEPING
THE BIG SLEEP.
- MEOW.
- ( moans in pain )
- MEOW. IN ABOUT ANOTHER FIVE
MINUTES, YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ALL TWISTED UP JUST LIKE
A YUMMY LITTLE PRETZEL.
- HEY, MILLIANA. I SCORED A
LITTLE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
- MEOW?
OH, A KITTY OF MY VERY OWN.
HE IS SUCH A LITTLE
CUTIE-WOOTIE.
- HAPPY.
- THAT'S ENOUGH. CALM DOWN
AND TIE ERZA UP.
- ALL RIGHT, DOLL.
TIME TO GET TO WORK.
- MEOW.
- SISTER...
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
FINALLY COMING HOME
TO THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
I KNOW JELLAL WILL BE
HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
- THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
DID THEY REALLY FINISH IT?
- Lucy: WHERE ARE YOU
TAKING HER? COME BACK.
SHE'S GONE.
( grunts )
I SWEAR I'M GOING TO GET
OUT OF THIS THING SOMEHOW.
( grunting continues )
YES. HERE WE GO.
OPEN GATE OF THE
GIANT CRAB. CANCER.
UH. OKAY. CANCER?
COME ON. FINE.
WHAT ABOUT TAURUS?
LOKE? PLEASE HELP.
- ( people clamoring )
- WHY CAN'T I USE MY KEYS?
IS IT BECAUSE OF THIS ROPE?
OW, WHAT THE...
- WHOOPS, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- HEY, WAS THAT YOU
THAT POKED ME?
- YEAH. I JUST HAPPENED TO HAVE
THIS LETTER OPENER IN MY POCKET
AND I THOUGHT I MIGHT
BE ABLE TO USE IT
TO CUT MY WAY
OUT OF THIS THING.
BUT I GUESS
I ACCIDENTALLY GOT YOU.
- Man: OH, I'LL TRY THAT, TOO.
- Woman: MAYBE WE CAN GET OUT.
- EVEN THOUGH HIS KNIFE'S INSIDE
THE CARD. I COULD FEEL IT.
- WHOA.
- SIR, I DON'T KNOW,
I MAY BE WRONG ABOUT THIS,
BUT I GET THE FEELING
OBJECTS INSIDE YOUR CARDS
MIGHT BE ABLE TO BREAK
THROUGH THEM.
- YOU THINK SO?
WHEN I DO THIS,
DOES IT LOOK TO YOU LIKE
THE KNIFE IS POKING OUT AT ALL?
- NO, IT LOOKS FLAT. BUT IF I
FELT IT THEN THAT MEANS
IT HAS TO HAVE SOME KIND OF
EFFECT ON WHAT'S OUTSIDE.
DO ME A FAVOR, I
NEED YOU TO TRY
AND CUT THROUGH THIS
ROPE WITH IT, OKAY?
- I'LL GIVE IT A SHOT.
- Man 2: YEAH COME ON, YOU CAN
DO IT. I JUST KNOW YOU CAN.
- ( screams )
PLEASE HURRY.
- I'M TRYING, LADY.
DON'T RUSH ME.
- SORRY BUT THIS HURTS.
WHOA, YOU DID IT.
THANKS A LOT. I OWE YOU ONE.
- YOU'RE WELCOME. YOU THINK
YOU CAN HELP US OUT NOW?
- I GOT TO RUN BUT I PROMISE
I'LL COME BACK TO HELP.
I GOT TO FIND THE BOYS.
I HOPE THAT GUY WAS
LYING AND THEY'RE OKAY.
WHAT HAPPENED? OH, NO.
SNAP OUT OF IT, GRAY.
TALK TO ME.
HE'S COLD.
( screams )
OH MY GOSH, I'M SO SORRY.
YOU'RE GOING BE OKAY.
I'LL FIX YOU UP IN
NO TIME I SWEAR.
( screams )
- Juvia: THERE'S
NO NEED TO PANIC.
- I REMEMBER YOU.
YOU'RE WITH THE ELEMENT FOUR.
- Gray: LUCY, WAIT.
SHE'S NOT OUR ENEMY ANYMORE.
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
I PULLED MY PRECIOUS GRAY INSIDE
OF ME TO ENSURE HIS SAFETY.
- IS IT JUST ME OR DOES
THAT SEEM REALLY WEIRD?
- ARE YOU JEALOUS, HE WAS
INSIDE OF ME AND NOT YOU?
- UH, NOT REALLY, NO.
- THIS DUDE CAST A DARKNESS
SPELL SO I CREATED AN ICE DECOY
TO DISTRACT HIM UNTIL I COULD
FIGURE OUT MY PLAN OF ATTACK.
- I WANTED TO KEEP THE REAL
GRAY SAFE FROM HARM,
SO, I PULLED HIM INSIDE
OF MY WATER LOCK
UNTIL I WAS SURE
THE DANGER HAD PASSED.
- YEAH, AND I COULDN'T DO
ANYTHING FROM IN THERE.
THANKS TO YOU,
THE CREEP GOT AWAY.
- ( gasps )
- NOW WHAT? DO YOU KNOW
WHERE EVERYONE ELSE IS?
- NO, I DON'T. IT'S BAD.
THEY TOOK ERZA AND HAPPY.
- ( screaming )
- Lucy: IS THAT?
- THE NERVE OF THAT GUY.
- Lucy: NATSU.
- Gray: NATSU.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- HEY, WHAT KIND OF JERK
SHOOTS PEOPLE IN THE MOUTH?
HUH? I MEAN SOMEONE
COULD GET REALLY HURT.
- UH, I THINK THAT'D KILL ANYONE
WHO WASN'T A WEIRDO LIKE YOU.
- I WOULD HAVE TO AGREE.
- I'LL SHOW THAT BLOCKHEAD.
HE'S NOT GETTING AWAY WITH THIS.
- FOLLOW HIM.
- WAIT. UH, DOES HE EVEN
KNOW WHERE HE'S GOING?
NATSU HAS A NOSE FOR PREY THAT'D
PUT WILD ANIMALS TO SHAME.
- I'M COMING FOR YOU, BLOCKHEAD.
( grunts )
- ( growls )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- MASTER JELLAL.
WE'VE RECEIVED WORD
THE MISSION TO RETRIEVE
ERZA HAS BEEN COMPLETED.
THEY ARE RETURNING AS WE SPEAK.
I MUST ASK, WHAT ARE WE TO GAIN
BY CAPTURING THAT TRAITOR?
DISPOSING OF HER WOULD HAVE BEEN
EASY WORK FOR SOMEONE
OF YOUR POWER.
- ( chuckles )
A RATHER PEDESTRIAN
APPROACH TO SOLVING
THE PROBLEM IN MY OPINION.
- YES SIR.
- HOWEVER, WITH THE TOWER
OF HEAVEN NOW COMPLETE,
ALLOWING HER TO LIVE WOULD PROVE
TO BE A THORNY ISSUE INDEED.
SO THE TIME HAS COME.
ERZA SCARLET IS THE
PERFECT SACRIFICE
TO ENSURE MY DREAMS
ARE MADE FLESH.
- THIS PLACE, WHERE ARE WE?
- INSIDE THE HOLD OF A
SHIP AT SEA.
- A SHIP?
- THAT'S RIGHT. AND OUR COURSE
IS SET FOR THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
- I SEE. I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
WOULD YOU PLEASE UNTIE ME?
I WON'T CAUSE ANY TROUBLE.
- I'M AFRAID I CAN'T. YOU'VE
PROVEN YOURSELF UNTRUSTWORTHY.
THAT WON'T HELP. MILLIANA'S
BINDINGS CAN SEAL MAGIC,
SO, YOU'RE STRUGGLING IN VAIN.
YOU'LL FIND YOU HAVE NO LUCK
IN BREAKING FREE FROM THEM.
THE EFFORTS WILL
JUST TIRE YOU OUT.
- FINE. I WON'T RESIST.
BUT PLEASE, SHO, WILL YOU ALLOW
ME TO REQUIP INTO MY ARMOR?
THE TOWER.
I'M AFRAID OF GOING BACK THERE.
I JUST WANT TO HAVE IT ON,
SO THAT I FEEL SAFE.
- BUT THE OUTFIT YOU
HAVE ON NOW IS LOVELY.
HONESTLY, I DIDN'T WANT
IT TO HAPPEN LIKE THIS.
- IT'S OKAY.
- I'VE MISSED YOU SO
MUCH. IT HURTS ME.
TELL ME. WHY?
WHY'D YOU DO IT?
WHY'D YOU BETRAY JELLAL?
- Erza: JELLAL.
- OVER HERE.
COME ON, HURRY UP.
- GEEZ. WE GOTTA TRY
TO BE QUIET, YOU DUMMY.
- HEY YOU'RE BEING EVEN LOUDER
THAN HE IS RIGHT NOW.
- AH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- COME ON, ERZA.
WE GOT TO MOVE QUICK
OR THE GUARDS WILL CATCH US.
- YEAH. I KNOW.
I WANT TO GO BUT I'M SCARED.
BECAUSE, I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO ALL THE OTHER KIDS.
THEY'RE DEAD.
- THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT. WE'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
- OH, JELLAL.
- WE'RE FINALLY GETTING
BACK OUR FREEDOM.
OUR FUTURE. OUR DREAMS.
LET'S GO. OKAY?
- OKAY.
- SINCE POOR LITTLE
HAPPY'S BEEN CATNAPPED,
I'VE GOT TO DO THIS
PREVIEW ALL BY MYSELF.
SO, I GUESS I SHOULD EXPLAIN
"OPERATION SAVE HAPPY AND ERZA".
IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE REALLY.
RUSH IN AND START
BEATING EVERYONE UP
TILL THEY TELL US
WHERE THEY ARE.
AND I'VE GOT THE PERFECT
CODE WORD, CHARGE.
LET'S GO IN AND GET THEM GUYS.
- Natsu and Happy:
NEXT TIME, JELLAL.
- Natsu: YOU'RE HERE. WHOA,
WHY'RE YOU ALL SCRUFFY LOOKING?
- Happy: I'VE GOT A LADY FRIEND
AND SHE LOVES HER SOME HAPPY.
- Natsu: AW, MAN, THAT WAS
A VISUAL IMAGE I DIDN'T NEED.