Now it's time for you to freeze!
Right after you burn!
[NARRATOR] Natsu and
Gray fight together
against Mard Geer Tartaros,
who has finally taken
on his Etherious form.
Sting and Rogue fought
an equally intense battle
against their former
guild master, Jiemma.
Who had been reborn as a demon.
[ROGUE, STING]
White Shadow Dragon Silk!
[JIEMMA groaning]
It's impossible!
How?!
[NARRATOR] Their struggle
was great, but in the end,
Sting and Rogue did
manage to fell Jiemma.
However, that finishing blow
was the last they'd strike.
The twin dragons collapsed,
putting their faith in
the Fairy Tail wizards
[ROGUE]
Natsu.
Gray.
[STING]
It's all... up to you now.
[NARRATOR] The team of fire and
ice redoubled their efforts,
assaulting Mard Geer Tartaros
with every ounce of
strength they had.
[NATSU yells]
[GRAY yells]
[NATSU yelling]
[GRAY yelling]
[MARD GEER] Prepare
yourselves for purgatory.
For I will invoke
the ultimate curse,
designed to destroy
Zeref himself!
[NATSU screams]
[GRAY groaning]
[MARD GEER]
The memory of death.
[NARRATOR]
All else having failed him,
Mard Geer resorted to
his most powerful curse.
One he'd planned to use
only on the Dark Lord Zeref.
[MARD GEER] Those afflicted
by the Memento Mori
no longer belong with the
living or with the dead.
They simply cease to exist.
[MARD GEER] You are now, and
forever will be... nothing.
The moment has arrived.
The ultimate curse has finally
been perfected and invoked.
Once E.N.D. has been revived,
I will fulfill my promise.
And then...
you will be destroyed,
Lord Zeref.
[MARD GEER] I've found you
worthy of my greatest curse.
Consider it an honor.
[gasps]
[MARD GEER gasping]
Your skin.
This can't be.
No.
[GRAY growling]
[MARD GEER] He's morphed
into a half-demon.
Is this Silver's power?
Did that traitorous corpse
somehow manage to counter
my ultimate curse?
[GRAY grunts]
Uh... Hey Natsu.
I know I... talk crap...
[NATSU gasps]
[GRAY]
But I've got faith in you.
I always have.
[GRAY]
If anyone can beat him,
it's you.
Hang in there.
[ICHIYA]
Man.
Status report.
There's no room for error
on a night like this.
Well said, boss.
We're on course for
the nearest Faces.
As for the message
from Fairy Tail,
I have it on a temporary file.
So what now?
We await your orders, sir.
The message.
Let's retransmit it.
Use the communication lacrima.
Make sure it's received
by every guild in Fiore.
Great idea, sir!
We'll need all
the help we can get.
[ICHIYA] At the end of
Fairy Tail's message,
I'd like you to
add the following:
"The fate of the continent
rests on this battle."
Gird your loins.
As Blue Pegasus' vanguard,
we must crush these Faces!
[GUILD MEMBERS]
Aye aye, Captain!
Where did those things come
from, and what are they?
Were they underground?
[MAN B]
All I know is they're creepy.
Can't be good.
I'm guessing those
big, white towers
are the Faces from that message.
Do you really think that they
can wipe out all magic?
Time is too short for us
to muse on the subject.
We must destroy them
without hesitation.
[MILLIANNA] Yeah, but
where do we even start?
There are so many of them,
and they're gigantic.
[KAGURA] First we put our
doubts aside, then we act!
[MILLIANNA]
Right.
Let's begin!
[OHBA] At least the citizens'll
be out of our way.
They've evacuated.
[LYON] A rather grotesque
sight, isn't it?
How the heck am I
supposed to take down
these ginormous
things all by myself?!
Now calm down and think.
If you're meant to do this
alone, then why are we here?
And stop your complaining
about how damn big they are.
Before I spin ya.
They aren't so big.
Allow me to show you.
[JURA]
Wait, Lyon!
[LYON]
Mm?
According to Sir
Ichiya's broadcast,
these things number
in the thousands.
We can't afford to take
them down one at a time.
We must act together.
Yes, sir.
Upon my name as a Wizard
Saint, I swear to you,
I will not allow magic to
be torn from this world.
Now, with our
strengths combined!
Hold nothing back.
Give it everything you've got!
I've got a hard
Drilling Rock For Ya!
And while we're at it,
eat some Plant Magic!
[cries]
In a world without magic,
I won't be able to drink
half as much as I like to.
Sobriety ain't wild at all!
Drunken Chop-Hanging Palm!
[ALL]
Now Let's get wild! Yeah!
Ah, Damn it.
I'm really gonna need
a drink after all this.
Care to start us off?
Yes, naturally.
I think I have just the memory.
Shrine of the Stormy Wind Fang!
[OLGA]
Lightning God!
Storm Charged Particle Cannon!
Take this!
[DOBENGAL]
Didn't even scratch it.
We have to keep trying
though! Don't give up!
All right troops! Let's do dis!
It's time for Twilight
Ogre to show the world
what we're made of!
[GUILD MEMBERS yelling]
[ALL]
It's no use!
Once I've slain you,
the mongrel's next!
Gray's not a demon!
He's a human being!
[NATSU growls]
[MARD GEER] Where did you
obtain so much power?
[NATSU grunting]
[NATSU growls]
Could this be your
Dragon Force?!
[NATSU] Igneel-Style
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Hidden Fire Form!
Flame Lotus Phoenix Sword!
[MARD GEER groaning]
[NATSU yells]
[yells]
Once I've vented all my rage,
you won't have a corpse to bury!
That was all the magic I had.
And you beat it.
Not too bad, for a demon.
[MARD GEER]
Be gone!
[NATSU]
Thing is... I have faith, too.
[MARD GEER gasps]
Gray, now!
[GRAY] Ice Demon...
Zero Destruction Bow!
[MARD GEER screams]
[MARD GEER groaning, screams]
[ERZA growls]
[KYOKA screams]
[KYOKA]
She's too strong!
[gasps]
[MARD GEER]
Kyoka.
[KYOKA]
It is done.
[panting]
[MINERVA (NEO)]
She's smiling.
Whoopididoo! We did it!
Every last one of
those Faces has blown!
[ERZA gasping]
We win, you lose! This is it!
The end of all you
worthless wizards!
Tartaros' wish is
finally comin' true!
[MIRAJANE whimpers]
[MIRAJANE]
In a world without magic...
What are we?
[MARD GEER groaning]
[NATSU sighs]
We did it.
[GRAY]
No. Not yet we haven't.
This ain't over until
I've destroyed E.N.D.
Right, I forgot.
Listen Gray,
I was actually supposed to get
ahold of that book for Igneel.
[GRAY] Sorry, but you're
not gettin' it.
Stop screwin' around.
Hand it over.
I'm serious, Natsu,
I'm not lettin' go.
I've got Tartaros's
master in this thing.
From what they say,
he's the most powerful demon
out of any of Zeref's books.
This might be the only chance
we'll ever get to erase him.
All I know is I made
Igneel a promise.
Now gimme the book.
I don't think so.
What is it now?
[GRAY]
Wait.
Could this be... the Faces?
So close.
But still too late.
I'm scared.
I mean without magic,
what'll we do?
Will we even be able
to talk still?
The screen changed!
Those must be the active Faces.
This isn't gonna be good.
Wait. So what'll happen now?
The age of magic is over.
There's nothing we can do.
Humanity won every last battle,
but still we lost the war.
What's going on?
They've been enveloped in light.
I don't get these things.
First they're indestructible,
and now they're
startin' to glow?
[RUFUS] I've no memory
to base this upon.
But It's my belief, they're
beginning to detonate.
I think you're right.
We gave it our all,
but we were just too late.
[MAKAROV]
What a tragic end.
[LUCY gasping]
Are you okay?
I dunno. I just got
weak all of a sudden.
Hey, do either of you guys feel
like something's missing?
Yeah, my telepathy's gone.
[DROY]
You don't think this means...
[gasps] Oh, no! My
Animal Soul spell.
It's been broken somehow.
Yeah, uh. I see that.
Dad. I can't move.
What's going on?
[MACAO]
Hang in there, son. Stay strong!
Ah, damn.
What I wouldn't give to
be ten years younger.
Idiot. This isn't an age thing!
[ELFMAN groans]
This is friggin' awful.
Losin' all my strength
is the least manly thing
that's happened to me.
Ah!
Damn it!
What's wrong? C'mon,
ya need to get up!
[LEVY]
I can't.
Don't you feel it?
Our magic's gone.
This can't be for real.
There's no way...
It seems the time
has finally come.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
I don't understand
what's wrong. I'm scared.
I can barely even move.
Our air is being drained
of Ether-nano.
That's how the Faces
do their work.
What a strange feeling.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[MAN C] The magic train
crashed outta nowhere!
[MAN D]
Somebody help! He's wounded!
[WOMAN A screams]
[MAN E]
Why can't we use magic?
[MAN F]
I can barely stand up.
[MAN G] Could it have something
to do with those faces?
[MAN H] We can't call for help.
The Lacrimas are failing!
[WOMAN B]
The entire town's gone dark!
[REN]
Target acquired!
[HIBIKI]
Trajectory set!
[EVE] Better make this quick!
We're losing energy!
The great Christina won't be
fazed by such a miniscule drain
on her magic power.
Aim... and fire!
[HIBIKI]
Target was unaffected chief!
[ICHIYA] We've only just
begun. Ready another.
Now, fire!
Man.
[MARD GEER] You do realize...
that this is only the beginning.
[BOTH gasp]
[MARD GEER] Once all
of your beloved magic
has been rendered obsolete,
the seal that binds my
master will finally break.
The moment when the mightiest of
the Etherious has been restored,
your species will find itself
devoid of both magic
and any means of opposing us.
No, damnit, no!
[gasps]
It's Acnologia.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[gasps]
[IGNEEL]
We haven't lost yet, humans.
Do not despair!
[gasps]
[REN]
We fired five volleys.
Why won't they break?
Christina's cannons are
the pride of Blue Pegasus,
and they didn't
even leave a mark.
So, should we abort
the mission, sir?
Between the cannon shots and
the draining Ether-nano,
we've lost too much power.
We're about to fall!
[ICHIYA]
So this is how it ends.
[GRANDEENEY]
You need to move!
[JENNY]
Huh? Who was that?
Hey, look!
Evasive maneuvers!
[ALL gasp]
Hot damn! What was that?!
A bird?
I sense Grandeeney!
[GRANDEENEY roars]
Now there's a sight. A dragon.
Thought they'd died out.
Come. We need to hurry.
Magnolia needs us.
[HAPPY gasps]
Those little Face thingies are
startin' to get crossed out.
Does this mean...
they're destroyed?
Metalicana's back.
[METALICANA roars]
I know Weisslogia's dead,
but somehow I'm picking
up on his energy.
And I can feel Skiadrum as well.
[IGNEEL]
My kindred are free at last.
[IGNEEL] We soar through the
skies of Ishgar once again!
[IGNEEL roars]
[WENDY]
It's a miracle!
[LISANNA, LUCY gasp]
[MARD GEER whimpers]
[GAJEEL]
Ha, ha.
[MAKAROV]
Mm...
[HAPPY]
Ha, ha!
[IGNEEL roars]
Incredible.
[LUCY]
After mysteriously reappearing,
the dragons made short work
of thousands of Faces.
Fairy Tail and our allies
rejoice in our victory
over Tartaros.
However, not every foe
has been eliminated.
Our excitement
proves short lived
when we're confronted
by the ones that remain
But as the battle wears on,
a flash of light glimmers
in the eastern sky.
Next Time: "Tartaros
Chapter Drops of Fire."
Finally, the true end arrives.