[NARRATOR] Natsu and friends
have found themselves
up against the Neo Oración Seis.
[NARRATOR] After failing
to obtain the Infinity Clock,
the team now realizes the
overwhelming power
of their foes.
[NARRATOR]
The seal held in place by
celestial wizards has been
lifted allowing the Infinity
Clock to reveal its true form.
[NARRATOR] And now
time has become chaotic.
♪
[GRAN DOMA] You think Cardinal
Lapointe was the one who
helped the Neo-Oración Seis
escape from prison?
[LAHAR] Yes, sir.
In fact, I'm certain of it.
With your permission,
I'd like to investigate further.
[GRAN DOMA]
I'm sorry but I simply
cannot allow you to do that.
I don't understand;
can you tell me why, sir?
It's for your own
safety; you don't
realize the power
that Zentopia holds.
[LAHAR] But, sir!
Well, I tried.
But no luck.
I know, I heard.
[LAHAR] I'm sorry.
I can't believe the Council
has rendered me powerless.
If I can't act in a crisis,
how am I supposed
to lead the Custody
Enforcement Unit?
Don't lose heart, man.
If they're not going
to help us then we'll
just have to do it without 'em.
Thanks, Doranbolt.
[MALE WORSHIPPER 146A]
Look, it's the archbishop!
[MALE WORSHIPPER 146B]
Please tell us what's happening,
Your Excellency!
[FEMALE WORSHIPPER 146A] Why has
time suddenly turned chaotic?
[OLD MAN WORSHIPPER 146A]
Does it have something to do
with the Infinity
Clock's appearance?
[MALE WORSHIPPER 146C]
Are these signs that the world
is coming to an end?
[MALE WORSHIPPER 146D]
Please give us
some answers, Archbishop!
Let me assure you, there
is no reason to be afraid.
This is simply the only way.
Zentopia can rectify the world.
[Worshippers murmur]
After the rectification,
the world shall be reborn.
From that point forward,
it shall follow a new path.
[BYRO] So that's
what they're planning.
Use the Neo-Oración Seis
to destroy churches,
eliminate all body-link
celestial wizards,
and then plunge time into chaos.
But will that truly
rectify the world?
[BYRO] Until I learn the
answer to that question,
I am duty-bound
to sacrifice the girl
and protect the Infinity Clock.
I'm afraid I have
no other choice.
[HAPPY] Time Spiral!
[ICHIYA] Man!
Hang in there,
Natsu and Lucy.
I, Ichiya, along with
this elite Fairy Tail team,
will save you from
the enemy's clutches!
Aw yeah, you tell 'em!
This is for my big sis
who's takin' on Racer
all by herself so we
can keep movin' forward!
Please stay strong.
We'll be there very soon.
I hope they're
gonna be okay.
[HAPPY] They'll be fine!
I know it!
How can you be
so sure about that?
I've just got faith
they will, ya know?
I believe that Natsu's
gonna be all right.
Wait, what
about Lucy?
As long as
Natsu's doin' okay,
there's no doubt in
my mind she is, too!
Yeah, I don't think we
have any reason to worry.
[WARREN] So let's get in there
and start kicking some butt.
You're extra manly
for sayin' that, Warren!
[GAJEEL] Geez, talk
about a bunch of idiots.
My Christina Advance,
the great magic bomber!
We are counting on you
to lead us into the fray!
Take us to the Grand
Cathedral of Zentopia!
[ICHIYA] Man!
[COCO] Are you gonna
tell me where we're going?
To see the archbishop!
For what reason?
To get payback, of course!
If he thinks he can get
away with usin' Michelle
like a puppet he's got
another thing comin'!
I'm gonna kick his butt!
The archbishop's butt?
[COCO] What happened?
You okay?
[NATSU] Up ahead.
[BUTT BOSS] Alright lackeys!
You ready to let it all out?
[BUTT LACKEY A] Yes, sir!
[BUTT LACKEY B] Yes, sir!
[NATSU] What're you
guys still doin' here?
True scoundrels never leave
empty-handed;
ain't that right, boys?
If we can't have
the Infinity Clock,
then we'll just have to
take a different treasure!
Do whatever you want,
I won't stop ya.
Yeah, like you could.
Listen up, lackeys!
It's time for us to
begin treasure-hunting!
[BUTT LACKEY A] Yes, sir!
[BUTT LACKEY B] Yes, sir!
[Butt Giggle Gang cries out]
[GUTMAN]
You guys're so weak I don't
even have to
use my Rupture magic!
[BUTT BOSS] You haven't
smelled the last of us--
What the--?
Who is that?
He's Gutman the Cleaner.
He's the what now?
[Gutman chuckles]
[GUTMAN] This is gonna be
fun 'cause the two of
you have a buncha magic in ya!
Be careful.
He's much more
powerful than he looks.
Oh, Really?
I'm all fired up now.
[SUB-CAPTAIN 146A] Captain!
Combat deployment is complete!
Okay.
Commence.
Firing!
Captain!
You're supposed
to do what I say.
Right!
Commence firing!
[Soldiers freak out}
[blast]
The military's men are
in a state of chaos as well.
Do you think it's because
of the Real Nightmare?
[GAJEEL] Screw this!
That Stupid clock!
I'm gonna pound its face in!
Yeah, good luck
with that, old man.
Whoa, when did Warren
become a muscle-head?
Now that's a
real man, for ya.
[WENDY ] Goodness.
Everyone looks so different!
You can say that again;
you're all grown up, Wendy!
[HAPPY ] And you've turned
into a cute, little raccoon dog!
Meanwhile, you've
turned into a mangy ol' mutt.
[ERZA] This is bad.
Everyone's been
affected by Real Nightmare!
Wait a minute.
I don't understand why nothing
bizarre has happened to me.
Hold on.
That's it!
Requip!
I should be able to
use the weapon Jean-Luc
gave me to counteract
Real Nightmare's waves!
He said it can ward off evil.
Here goes!
[GRAY ] Geez, did ya
have to hit us so hard?
[ALL] We're back to normal!
Seems kinda odd
that they don't have anyone
standing guard over
the archbishop's quarters.
Who cares? It made
our job easier, right?
What is that?
[GILDARTS] Dunno.
Never seen anything like it.
[LAKI] Shh!
The archbishop's here!
Well, if you ask me,
it's time for us to be direct.
[LAKI] Huh?
No, wait!
[GILDARTS] So you're
the archbishop.
[ARCHBISHOP] Let me assure you,
there's no reason to be afraid.
This is simply the only way.
Zentopia can rectify the world.
[GILDARTS] I've got
some questions for ya.
You think you can
give me a straight answer?
[ARCHBISHOP] Let me assure you,
there's no reason to be afraid.
This is simply the only way
Zentopia can rectify the world.
Hey, are you even
listenin' to me, old man?
[ARCHBISHOP] Let me assure you,
there's no reason to be afraid.
This is pointless.
What in the heck
is wrong with him?
I think it's pretty likely
that somebody could be
using some kind of mind
control spell on him, don't you?
[GILDARTS] Who's that guy?
[LAKI] His name is Lapointe.
He's a Zentopian cardinal.
[LAPOINTE]
And if I'm not mistaken,
you're Gildarts Clive
of the Fairy Tail guild.
[GILDARTS] Wow.
I must be even more
famous than I thought.
I never would've
imagined that a
Zentopian cardinal
would know my name.
[GILDARTS] Sorry but I can't
sign any autographs right now.
I'm a little busy, you see.
[LAPOINTE] I commend
you and your colleague
for making it this far.
But, you've seen too much so
I'm afraid you will have to die.
Go ahead and try.
C'mon, show me what you've got.
[RACER] I'm too fast.
You can't...
keep up... with me.
[RACER] Stay away!
Stay away!
Just give up the fight.
There's no way you'll beat me.
[RACER] Faster.
Make me even faster!
[MIRAJANE] What did you do?
He's increased
his speed somehow!
[Racer cackles]
I admit you're
fast... However.
[RACER] I don't understand.
What happened?
How are you faster than me?
I'm not running away.
[MIRAJANE] Unlike you,
I'm moving forward.
[MIRAJANE] I have a purpose.
The desire to save my
friends pushes me
to fight harder and faster.
[MIRAJANE] If I may ask,
what are you running from?
[RACER] I'm not sure.
I've spent my
entire life running.
It's all I know.
[RACER]
I was always running away.
[MIRAJANE] I know what it is,
you've been running
from yourself.
From... myself?
[MIRAJANE] Yes.
You're fleeing from your past.
[MIRAJANE] All the pain,
distress, and the fear.
[MIRAJANE] I know what
it's like to try to escape it.
I used to do the
same thing myself.
I tried to run,
but it never helped.
[MIRAJANE] Believe me when I say
I understand your heartache.
[MIRAJANE] Where are you going?
No one's chasing you.
[MIRAJANE] There's no
need to run anymore.
[KINANA]
Someone's calling out to me.
[KINANA] But I wonder who.
I have to find them.
[MIDNIGHT]
It seems Racer has fallen.
Cobra, Angel, you
must stop them at once.
[GUTMAN] We gotta stay
faithful to Zentopia's doctrine,
silly-billy.
In other words,
we can never doubt it.
Never ever.
[NATSU] But what'll you do
if someone does doubt it?
[GUTMAN] You really wanna know?
Heathens go boom!
What is that?
It's Rupture magic.
Get away from it!
[GUTMAN] It expands
all the magic power
inside of my target
'til they go boom boom!
[Natsu cries out]
[COCO] Are you all right?
[GUTMAN] I'll clean away anyone
who goes against Zentopia.
Starting with you!
That's what you think!
[GUTMAN] I'm not scared of you!
[COCO] Leave him alone!
[GUTMAN] Oh, do
you wanna dance, too?
[GUTMAN] Time to rupture!
[GUTMAN]
You're gonna keep dancin'
as long as you've
got magic power!
[GUTMAN] Uh-oh.
[NATSU] We don't
have the time to be
messin' around with this loser!
[GUTMAN]
Then I'll speed things up.
Ready for your last dance?
How come I can't move?
[MARY] 'Cause I
totally immobilized you!
[NATSU] No way!
[GUTMAN]
What are you doin' to me?
I thought everybody who opposed
the archbishop was like, evil.
But with guys like you and the
Neo-Oración Seis hangin' around.
I totally can't tell
who's evil anymore.
I'm totally confused now.
Me, too.
[GUTMAN] I don't need to
move to use Rupture magic!
Watch out!
[Mary cries out]
[MARY] Immobilizing
people isn't all I do!
[MARY] Watch this!
Get outta here, now!
But Hughes...
Please.
This might be the
only chance for one of
us to find out what's
really going on!
Don't worry
about me just go!
Okay!
C'mon!
[CAPTAIN 146B] It's Fairy Tail!
Keep them away
from the cathedral!
Hurry men!
Fire!
[ICHIYA] Never underestimate
the Christina Advance!
Man!
[HAPPY] Oh, wow!
[BYRO] We meet again Fairy Tail.
[BYRO] Though my faith
in Zentopia is wavering.
I still have a duty to uphold.
I've no choice but to stop them.
Go, Kanaloa!
You've got to be joking.
Your octopus is no match for us!
Man!
Didya see that?
It deflected all of our shots!
[ICHIYA] Oh, no.
What a perilous parfum!
Hurry and knock
it off of the ship!
[BYRO] I'll leave you
to handle this, Kanaloa.
[BYRO] In the meantime,
I'm going to pay a visit to the
archbishop and
demand some answers.
Now what?
We don't want a
repeat of seven years ago!
I have no other choice;
deploy Spiral Anchors!
Man!
I shall defeat it by sacrificing
the Christina Advance.
[ICHIYA] Save yourselves
before it's too late.
[WENDY] But we
can't leave you behind!
[ICHIYA] Just do as I say!
You heard him; let's go!
[ALL] Right!
Good luck.
My friends... man!
[explosion]
[WENDY] Ichiya.
[GRAY] That jerk!
Actin' all cool
'til the very end!
[ELFMAN] He was
the manliest of men!
Surviving danger
is what Ichiya does best,
so I'm sure
that he'll be fine.
Chin up, everyone!
Let's go find Natsu and Lucy!
[ALL] Yeah!
Let me assure you,
there's no reason to be afraid.
This is simply the only way.
Zentopia can rectify the world.
[NATSU] Hold on a second!
[GILDARTS] Natsu.
I'm surprised to see that
you broke out as well...
...Coco.
Cardinal.
And you...
I know exactly who you are.
[NATSU] Huh?
You're Natsu Dragneel.
A Dragon Slayer wizard.
Hey, wait a minute,
I know that smell.
No way...
You smell just like
that Master Zero guy!
You don't really
think it's him, do you?
[Lapointe laughs]
I dunno whether this
creep's "Master Zero" or not.
But he is the one who's been
controlling the archbishop.
[ERZA] What is it?
I just heard Gildarts' voice.
Apparently Zentopia's
archbishop,
is being controlled
by Cardinal Lapointe!
[ERZA] He is?
[BYRO THINKS] His holiness is
being manipulated by Lapointe?
All this time,
he's been using his authority
to take advantage of everyone.
Including me!
[BYRO] I'm not going to
let him get away with this!
[NATSU]
I just realized somethin'.
If you're controlling the
archbishop then you must be the
one who decided to use the
phony Michelle to trick us.
[LAPOINTE] And what if I am?
Then you're goin' down!
I'm gonna burn you to a crisp!
[GILDARTS] Hang on, kid.
If anyone fights him,
it should be me.
[NATSU] Aw c'mon, Gildarts!
Let me do it!
You don't have a prayer.
[GILDARTS] Laki!
[LAPOINTE] Since you two
seem to enjoy fighting,
let's see what happens
when you exchange blows.
[NATSU]
We ain't fightin' each other!
[Lapointe laughs]
[LAPOINTE] Defy me
and I will kill the young lady.
[NATSU] No way.
[GILDARTS] Let her go! She's
got nothin' to do with this!
[LAPOINTE] What?
[NATSU] Octo-geezer!
[BYRO] How dare you
try to deceive me, Lapointe!
Byro.
[IMITATIA] They're coming.
[IMITATIA] Your beloved friends
are on their way to you.
[LUCY] My friends.
From Fairy Tail?
So they were able
to find a way to get inside!
[IMITATIA] Yes,
but I'm afraid they're
going to lose their lives.
What do you mean?
Why are they going
to lose their lives?
[IMITATIA]
Because of you, Big Sister.
[LUCY] Huh?
[IMITATIA]
They care about you too much.
So I'm going to
have to kill them.
[LUCY] No.
Why?
[IMITATIA] I won't
let anyone else have you.
[IMITATIA] Big Sister.
You belong to me!
[LUCY] Michelle.
♪
[NATSU] Everyone
keeps changin' ages!
What the heck is goin' on?
[HAPPY] Time got all messed up!
We gotta hurry and stop
it before things get really bad!
[NATSU] Would you
mind telling me what
you mean by "really bad"?
[HAPPY] Well, uh.
Are you sure you
wanna go into that?
[NATSU] I can't get all fired up
unless I've got a good reason.
[HAPPY] Gimme a break!
Okay fine, what about
Lucy bein' in danger?
Ain't that enough reason for ya?
[HAPPY AND NATSU] Next time:
To the Infinity Castle!
[NATSU] Guess it's not enough
to get my blood boiling.
I mean, I'm worried and all
but I'm not "fired up," y'know?
[HAPPY] Would you
quit bein' a big dummy
and just go save Lucy already?
[NATSU] Yeah yeah.