[NATSU]
We've dealt with Face.
And your little city just
crashed and burned.
Looks like it's about time
for you boys to surrender.
I know you.
Nah. You couldn't
possibly be him.
Ah! Who, that guy?
He's the jerk who froze
the giants' village!
Oh, yeah, and on top
of that he froze me!
[GAJEEL]
Pathetic.
Can it!
[GAJEEL] I gotta say though.
The guy smells like you.
He has the same parfum
as my darling Gray?
[GRAY gasps]
Gray, no!
I like this one. I think
I'll take him with me!
What? Where?
[JUVIA]
Where'd they go?
[GAJEEL]
No tellin'.
The nerve of that man.
I've liked Gray for
much longer than he has.
[KEYES]
How fascinating.
[TEMPESTER]
You've turned your backs.
Quite arrogant, considering
the calamity before you.
[GAJEEL, JUVIA, NATSU grunt]
Vwoosh.
[JUVIA gasping]
[LUCY screams]
[TEMPESTER]
Uh!
[GAJEEL] Good luck blowin'
me away. Iron Dragon Club!
[GAJEEL grunts]
[NATSU grunts]
Water Slicer!
How're we supposed
to hurt that?!
[GAJEEL yells]
[KEYES] A water wielder.
Even more fascinating.
Keep your guards up, all right?
Shake and Rumble.
[NATSU groaning]
So strong.
[NATSU]
I'm fired up now!
Let's do this!
[GAJEEL]
Right!
[JUVIA] Let's make them tell us
where that old man took my Gray!
Come on!
[JUVIA, NATSU, GAJEEL yell]
[KEYES]
This is far from over.
Uh... Well isn't
this pathetic.
I've managed to separate
myself from my comrades.
And right when they need
me the most. Disgraceful.
Uh?! Is that the sound
of distant thunder I hear?
What shall I do if it is?
I lost all the kiwis I
saved for emergencies.
I'm doomed!
[PANTHERLILY] A crate of
kiwis ripe for the taking!
Wait. These aren't kiwis at all!
They're cannonballs!
How could I have mistaken
these useless lumps of metal
for sweet, nourishing kiwis?
Oh for shame.
[PANTHERLILY]
Stay strong.
You must not let desperation
make a fool of you again.
[PANTHERLILY]
None of these are kiwis.
[HAPPY groans]
[PANTHERLILY]
Uh?! Huh...
Hey Happy! It's good to see you.
I'm glad you're all right.
Unfortunately, I've been
separated from Gajeel And I...
--[HAPPY whimpers]
--[PANTHERLILY] Uh...
[screams]
[HAPPY] My head got
knocked up by a fungus.
Just like that old Midi
woman said it would.
Knew I should'a paid her.
Can you... feel it move?
Oh, no, what if Carla doesn't
think I'm handsome anymore?
No, uh listen...
As skull based fungi go, that
one looks almost 'dapper'.
Ya mean it?
[PANTHERLILY]
Yeah... Sure.
Why not?
[HAPPY]
"Look what I found, Grandma,
an Exceed with a
mushroom in his head."
"Good eye, child, that'll
make a delicious side dish.
Let's cut it off and
throw it in the skillet
for dinner tonight."
So, it's stuck there, is it?
[HAPPY]
Aye.
[PANTHERLILY] I apologize in
advance if you lose your ears!
[HAPPY] Woah woah woah! Can't
we try something else first?!
[PANTHERLILY]
We can.
[HAPPY] Aren't we gonna
count off or something?
C'mon you gotta
give me a warning!
If you keep this up you're gonna
pop off my entire frickin' head!
I. Don't. Want. To. Die!
Shroom one. Us zero.
Maybe I can make it trendy.
[PANTHERLILY]
Best not to lie to yourself.
[HAPPY sighs] At least
Carla hasn't seen it yet.
What'll she say?
Ha, ha, ha!
[FRANMALTH] It may have
looked like I was dead,
and I did become quite weak
after Hell's Core went kaboom,
but I used my curse to force
this feline to absorb me!
Now, safe behind the fuzzy
ears of my foe, I'll wait.
These kitties will lead
me to their friends,
and then I'll strike!
[MACAO]
Hey, Cana! Check this out!
Whoa. Last I remember,
we were in that cube.
Now it's been destroyed?
Doesn't look like it
made much distance.
Yeah, we're still close to
Magnolia. Just south. I think.
Has anybody seen the master?
[DROY] I heard that he was
heading for the guild hall.
[WAKABA]
I wonder why.
I'm sure it's just a smoking
pile of rubble now.
[MAKAROV]
What a morbid sight this is.
Even Kardia Cathedral.
The pride of this town.
[MAKAROV]
The second master's final words.
"It's not over yet."
"Makarov must
unleash the light."
[WENDY gasps]
Where am I?!
Wendy!
Carla, hey. Wait.
Didn't we...?
[WENDY]
How are we still alive?
What about Face?!
We did stop it, didn't we?
[DORANBOLT]
Yes. You certainly did.
[WENDY]
Uh!? Doranbolt. You're here?
You two were heroic, truly.
Doranbolt showed up the instant
before Face detonated.
He's the reason we're alive.
I'm just glad I was able
to made make it in time.
Wait, so...
Carla? Would you be
my friend again?
Of course I would.
I can't believe it.
Neither can I.
Our adventure isn't
over after all.
[CARLA]
No. It's just begun.
[WENDY, CARLA cry]
[WENDY] We owe you our
lives. We won't forget.
Yeah. Listen.
If anyone deserves a break
it's you two, but...
[DORANBOLT]
This fight. It's not over yet.
[BOTH gasp]
[HAPPY] There's gotta be some
way to get this off'a me, right?
[PANTHERLILY]
I wouldn't mess with it.
Thing might spread its spores.
Your entire body could end
up covered in mushrooms.
That's a nice image.
[FRANMALTH] I'm confident
in my king, of course,
but I'm confused
by what he said.
Our plans remain unchanged. The
Face's activation is imminent.
[FRANMALTH]
I thought we were wrong
about where Face would appear.
But what if we weren't?
What if the Face we charted
just hadn't appeared yet?
[WENDY whimpers]
[WENDY]
No.
[FRANMALTH] They stopped one
Face. But only one of 'em!
How many are there?
There's no official count
on the number, but...
thousands, at least.
[MARD GEER]
There it is.
[MARD GEER] The engine
of humanity's demise.
Appeared at last,
in all its glory.
We fought so hard.
Nearly gave our lives to destroy
just one of these things.
But thousands remain.
We've lost. It's ov--
Don't say it, Carla.
[WENDY]
I'm tired of despair.
[WENDY] I'm done with it.
It doesn't help anything.
Wendy. Your hair.
I'm through shedding tears. I've
cried enough for one lifetime.
Our comrades are determined.
They're fighting.
I'll fight with them.
[BOTH growling]
What has happened
to you, Minerva?
I am now called Neo-Minerva.
For as you can see,
I have been reborn.
As the ultimate wizard!
[MINERVA (NEO)]
Territory!
[ERZA screams]
Was that as good for you as
it was for me? Sweet Erza--
--[ERZA yells]
--[MINERVA (NEO) screams]
[ERZA growls]
[MINERVA (NEO) yells]
[MINERVA (NEO)] I gave
everything for strength.
Including my feeble humanity!
Then explain to me...
Just what it is
you're fighting for!
[groaning]
[JIEMMA]
You're a disgrace.
[MINERVA (NEO) gasps]
[MINERVA crying]
[JIEMMA]
You're of my blood.
So tell me why it is
that you're so weak!
[MINERVA (NEO) gasping]
[MINERVA]
I'm sorry, I don't know.
Please forgive me,
Father! I'm so sorry!
[JIEMMA] If you cared
to learn this lesson,
you'd know better than to beg.
[MINERVA yelps] I wasn't
thinking! Please don't be angry.
Do you continue pleading to defy
me or are you simply stupid?
You whimper like a victim...
Sabertooth has no
use for victims.
place for the weak.
[MINERVA (NEO) yells]
[cries]
[JIEMMA] Our guild demands
but one thing. Strength.
We cull the weak. And I
do not allow exceptions.
Prove your strength to earn your
place or get out of my sight.
I am not weak!
[JIEMMA] You reveal your
weakness in every way.
Stop waiting to get
hit, and attack!
Do not relent. Do not defend.
Victims need defending.
Tigers need the hunt.
[MINERVA groaning]
[JIEMMA]
Stop acting hurt.
[MINERVA]
Uh...
Get on your feet right now
before I break your legs myself.
[JIEMMA]
Fingers! Continue!
[FINGERS]
Right!
[FINGERS] You'll have
to do more than jump!
[MINERVA gasps]
Absolute domain magic...
She used Territory...
[FINGERS yells]
[FINGERS gasps]
[MINERVA]
Uh...
Are you okay?
[JIEMMA] Not for long
he isn't. Finish him!
[MINERVA]
Uh?!
Only the weak can be defeated.
And the weak are
like insects to us.
Lowly creatures not worthy
of your time or sympathy.
He's worth the heel of
your boot and no more.
But why? Fingers is a
friend ours, isnt he?
[JIEMMA] "Friend" is a word
made for and by the weak.
My daughter has no need for
such words. Try these instead.
We aim to stun the heavens,
to rouse the land beneath us
and silence the raging seas.
For you see that is
the Sabertooth way.
[MINERVA]
But do we have to be so--
[JIEMMA] If you can't relieve
him of his shame, I will.
Be gone.
[MINERVA]
Uh!
Wha... What'd he
do wrong? [cries]
Stop crying.
[JIEMMA]
Cease your crying this instant!
There is nothing weaker
you can do than shed tears!
How many times must
I tell you this?
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
[MINERVA (NEO)] I can't be weak.
I have to be stronger than you!
[ERZA]
That will never happen!
The years I've spent teaching
you have been wasted.
But a place may do
what I could not.
These woods are filled
with vicious beasts.
Either they will strip
you of your tears,
your heart, and your weakness.
Or they will strip
you of your life.
Once your tears have dried
for good, you may return.
[MINERVA]
I'm sorry Father.
Forgive me, I'll
do better. I will.
[JIEMMA] You're no daughter of
mine. You're weak!
I cull the weak! I should crush
you like the insect you are!
[gasps]
[MONSTERS roar]
[MINERVA]
We aim to stun the heavens.
To rouse the land beneath us.
And to silence the raging seas.
For you see.
For you see. That is
the Sabertooth way.
Get it together!
[ERZA] Back at the
Grand Magic Games,
you crossed a lot of lines.
I can't forgive you for
hurting my friends,
but I can understand.
You wanted to do what's
best for your guild.
Minerva. My fists weep for you.
They protest every blow.
They're asking for a reason
as to why we have to fight.
[MINERVA (NEO)]
There isn't one.
And I'm out of fight.
I have a request.
Please free me from my shame
and show me to my death.
[MINERVA (NEO)]
I've always been weak.
And weakness is
easily corrupted.
Just look at what
I've done to myself.
I beg you...
[ERZA]
Horns or no, you're human.
Someone is out there waiting
for you to come home.
I m sure of it.
[MARD GEER] This is why
I so despise your kind.
It's bad enough that you go
through birth and death and rot.
Do you have to speak of it, too?
It's repugnant.
Do I know you?
[ERZA] Wait, I've heard
that voice before.
[ERZA gasps]
The Underworld King, Mard Geer!
[MARD GEER]
What a bother.
The Celestial Spirit King's
got all that refuse
we had swept away
popping back up
through the woodwork.
Curse that meddlesome boor.
Luckily, I have a bit
of time to spare.
More than enough to clear
you away once and for all.
So you're behind all this.
[ERZA screams]
What kind of curse
does he wield?
[MARD GEER]
I'll start right here.
Minerva!
[MINERVA (NEO)]
Erza. Run.
[ROGUE]
We're just in time.
[ERZA gasps]
[STING]
Or fashionably late.
We came to bring
ya home. M'lady!
I'm really diggin' those horns!
You belong with us,
back at Sabertooth.
And please never
leave us again!
[MARD GEER]
Well...
[STING] Now that is one
mean-lookin' fella'.
Guess he must be our
enemy. Right, Erza?
His energy. It's like nothing
I've sensed before.
C'mon, ladies.
The twin dragons've got this
clown; you need a break.
We packed an extra lunch.
Uh...
[ERZA] Someone is out there
waiting for you to come home.
I'm sure of it.
[LUCY] Thousands of face bombs
are set to detonate in an hour.
Newly arrived at the scene of
this unprecedented crisis,
Sabertooth's Twin
Dragons now challenge
the Underworld King with
anger in their fists.
Gray and Silver's fight begins
with Silver flinging words
as well as curses.
Words of revelation. The kind
that tear your heart out.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
The Boy's Tale"
A woeful truth shines
light on despair.