[LEADER] Hungry Wolf
Knights, Commence Operation
Fifteen-hundred.
They're Executioners?
They don't exactly
look the part.
Trust me, they're
very good at their jobs...
If the rumors are true,
then we're facing some
relentless hunters.
A group of royal
execution machines.
The Hungry Wolf Knights!
They're the reason
it's impossible to
leave this cursed place...
Alive, anyway.
[LEADER] By the
authority granted to us
by the Kingdom of Fiore, we,
The Hungry Wolf Knights,
will now carry
out your sentence.
[NATSU] Previously,
on Fairy Tail!
[NARRATOR] Behind the
spectacle and fanfare of
the Grand Magic Games,
a secret plan,
The Eclipse Project,
was set in motion.
The aim: to change
history as we know it.
What lies beyond
it is time itself...
It will allow us to travel four
hundred years into the past,
and slay Zeref before he
gains the power of immortality.
His destruction is
our ultimate goal.
But.... How's
that even possible?
[NARRATOR] However, there was
opposition to this radical plan,
spearheaded by
Defense Minister Darton.
Fearful of the consequences that
changing the past may bring
upon humanity, he
imprisoned Lucy and Yukino,
whose celestial magic
was vital to its success.
A two-pronged
strategy. Nicely done.
[MAKAROV] Godspeed my children!
We're counting on you!
[NARRATOR] But on the
last day of the tournament,
Natsu and his team were able to
rescue the two young ladies.
Unfortunately, as they searched
for the massive dungeon's exit,
the group found themselves
in even greater danger.
Beautiful...
What is this?!
Wendy!
[WENDY] Hey. What
happened to me?
Where am I?
I'm trapped in here.
Why can't I move?!
[COSMOS] Soon you'll
dance with the grim reaper...
As my Corpse Flower
blooms from your blood!
Just hang
in there, Wendy!
I'm gonna get you
outta that thing!
[NATSU yells]
[COSMOS giggles]
[COSMOS] How ungraceful!
Besides, it's
far too late...
The digestion has begun and
her sweet life is ending.
I cannot let you
get away with this!
Don't do it, Carla!
It's too dangerous!
[COSMOS] There's
no need to worry.
She will soon be reincarnated.
Her remains will turn
into dazzling blooms.
She's gonna
turn into flowers?
Whoa...
[FLOWERS giggling]
[CARLA] Stop daydreaming!
Oh?
Why are you just
standing around?
Your little friend
is in hot water.
[MIRAJANE] He's got a point.
I'll go help Wendy...
Can you stay behind
and fight him?
[PANTHERLILY] Roger.
I got big boy.
Sounds like a party!
[PANTHERLILY] Don't get cocky,
you're still small potatoes.
[NEPPA] Sploosh!
[blows landing]
I'm coming,
Wendy! Hold on!
[HAPPY]
Fairy Tail vs. Executioners!
[distant explosions]
Haa!
Oh my. Look at her!
Such a dangerous beauty.
[MIRAJANE] Wendy!
Ungh!
Thanks, Mira...
Whoa, that was
awesome! Way to go!
Amazing!
Are you okay?
I am. All thanks to you.
[NATSU] Nice job, Mira!
I don't believe it.
That's her?
[MIRAJANE] This is nuts!
Is it just me, or does she
look a lot like Lisanna?
[YUKINO] Huh?
[LUCY] Well, now
that you mention it...
Lisanna? Who's that?
She's my little sister.
Wow.
What strange magic.
[LEADER] Yes. Take over
spells are unusual, indeed.
[CARLA] That's just one of
Mirajane's many forms!
[HAPPY] Yeah, like Satan Soul!
This one's called Sitri,
and it's her most
butt-kicking She-Devil form!
I never would have
known that was her.
Oh yeah!
She's a full fledged
S-Class Fairy Tail wizard.
And once she's
in this form,
there's nothing to be afraid of!
[HAPPY] Yeah, right.
Just don't make her mad.
Indeed. She's
probably the most
frightening one
of all of us here.
[KAMIKA] Freeze inside
my paper blizzard!
Oh, I got
somethin' for that!
[LUCY] Let 'em
have it, Natsu!
[gasping]
[NATSU] Lucy!
I'll cut it down!
[LEADER] I see...
So the feline's sword can
change sizes as well.
Gosh!
Well, now that that's
outta the way,
I can focus on chubby again.
[NEPPA] Pop! Pop!
Hey, pussycat!
Just one sploosh,
and I can melt all that
fur right off of ya!
In that case, I guess
I'm just gonna have
to cut you off first!
Paper Blizzard:
Purple Dance!
What is this?
I feel like
I'm paralyzed!
It's all over me!
It's some kind of
status ailment spell!
Every single piece holds
the spirit of confinement.
Our harmony
is quite lovely...
Grow Flow!
That's huge!
Is that a plant
or a monster?
Is it some kind
summoning magic?!
Feast, my
pet... Gorge away.
Let their lives
nourish you!
It's sucking us up!
[ALL screaming]
Ahh! Runnin'
away, are ya?
Your loss. I woulda killed
ya a whole lot quicker!
[NEPPA laughs]
[PANTHERLILY] Shut your mouth!
[YUKINO screams]
[MIRAJANE] Yukino! Wendy!
[WENDY] I got ya!
O sky, cleanse us
of our ailments.
Restore our bodies.
With your shining light! Rays!
[LUCY] I'm glowing!
I can move!
Which means
that we can fight!
[LUCY] What do we do?!
[PANTHERLILY] Destroy it!
[NATSU] All right,
now you're talkin'!
You Ready?!
[MIRAJANE &amp; PANTHERLILY] Yeah!
Fire Dragon
Brilliant Flame!
[LUCY] Uh-oh...
I think this situation's
about to get much worse!
[HISUI gasps]
[SOLDIER A] No way!
Is that true?!
[SOLDIER B] Yeah! The
dispatch just came in!
That's great news!
[SOLDIER D] It'll all
be taken care of.
They should be able
to wipe out that scum
in no time.
Princess! The
Hungry Wolf Knights
have been sent down to
execute the prisoners.
[SOLDIER A] They're
as good as dead now.
[SOLDIER B] No kidding.
I'm sure the knights will make
easy work of them. Mm-hmm.
[HISUI thinking] No.
This isn't going at
all as I'd planned.
I hope you can
make it out alive...
Please be safe, Arcadios.
[NATSU gasps]
[NATSU] I'm gettin'
kinda sick of the fallin'.
Hey! Is everybody okay?!
[LEADER] It would appear
that blast of yours
has scattered your
comrades far and wide.
But my subordinates are
single-minded in their work.
Rest assured none of you
will ever leave this place.
I came down
here to get Lucy
and I'm not gonna
leave without her.
But since you're here, I guess
I gotta deal with you first
if I wanna get
anything else done.
So why don't ya tell
me who's butt I'm kickin.'
[LEADER] A criminal like you
doesn't deserve to know my name!
[WENDY] Oh no!
I don't see anybody
else down here!
\What am I gonna do?
I can't even sense their power.
[COSMOS] Exquisite.
Perhaps...
delicately beautiful
is a better description.
But still...
You must die.
[PANTHERLILY] This is bad...
I should've tried
to stay with them.
How careless of me.
And without their gate keys,
Lucy and Yukino are
completely defenseless.
If I'm gonna help them, I
gotta get you out of my way.
[NEPPA] Oh yeah?
Well, I see it a
li'l differently.
I think you're
in MY way...
But not for long!
[MIRAJANE] Lucy!
Yukino! Can you hear me?!
[MIRAJANE] Where did they go?
I need to find them
before those knights do.
You should be worried
about your own safety.
Don't you think?
[MIRAJANE] I'm
sure I'll be fine...
Tell me... do you happen to know
where my friends
ran off to?
The same place
you're going...
to the afterlife.
[HAPPY] Oweee...
[CARLA] I certainly
could've done without that.
Natsu overdid it?
Big surprise.
[YUKINO] I wonder how
far down we've fallen.
[HAPPY] I think we're
still in creepy-land.
[LUCY] Wait, did we get
separated from the others?!
We gotta find them!
[CARLA] And as per usual. I
find myself in the middle
of the most defenseless
bunch imaginable.
And without
our gate keys,
we can't summon any
spirits to help us.
Come on, guys.
We need to start
looking right now.
Those killers are down
here somewhere...
We gotta find Natsu before--
[HAPPY screams]
[LUCY] What's the matter?
[CARLA] Stop this
foolishness at once!
I'm not doing this
on purpose, I feel like
I'm getting caught like
a poor, delicious fishy!
I got one!
Him again?!
I love fish!
But I'm a cat,
for cryin' out loud!
Oh yeah?
I smell fish!
Do I look like one? Notice
the fur and pointy ears?!
Hoo boy!
You got a really
nice catch, there.
[HAPPY] What
are you doing?!
Hey! I was saving
that for lunch!
[UOSUKE] Too bad!
[LUCY] He's so weird. And
he really doesn't seem to
fit in with the rest of
his scary crew, either.
He's about as
terrifying as Happy.
But still...
[HAPPY] You're really
gonna take it?
[UOSUKE] Give it here.
[HAPPY shouts]
No, Happy!
What is the matter
with this guy?!
[UOSUKE] My name is Uosuke!
That's not what
she was asking.
Even without magic,
I bet we could beat up
this fish-stealer.
Seems likely.
You better
hush or else...
You're gonna make me mad.
[HAPPY] Aw man...
He's not all there, is he?
[LUCY] Happy's right...
We can beat this weirdo.
or at least outsmart him.
Do you know anything
about fighting?
Yes! I actually
have had a little bit
of training in
hand-to-hand combat.
[ARCADIOS] No...
Please... Don't do it!
Run away!
Colonel Arcadios?
You mustn't
engage him... Uosuke.
He's too strong...
I've heard tales of his magic.
He annihilates his victims.
not even their bones
are left behind.
Huh?!
This goofball?!
You just made me mad.
[LEADER] Before
I take your life.
you should pray
forgiveness for your sins.
[NATSU] It's cool...
I don't remember doin'
much sinnin' in my life.
[LEADER] Reflect on
your past carefully.
Clear your conscience.
I will allow you a
moment to do this.
before I strike you down.
I don't need it.
I said I don't remember
doin' any bad stuff, so
let's get this over with.
[MAKAROV moaning]
Are you feelin'
okay, master?
I'm fine.
But for some reason,
all those letters of apology
I've had to write just
came flooding back to me.
We've caused
so much trouble...
so much destruction...
so many regrettable decisions...
Well, there's no
denyin' it...
But let's focus on the
positives right now, okay?
What's he talkin'
about, mama?
It's nothing you need
to worry about just yet.
I wonder what's goin'
on with Natsu and his team.
They've been in there
for kind of a long time.
We should've heard
something by now.
We have to maintain
our faith in them.
And never give up hope.
[MAVIS] We also need
to have a plan of action
for when they do come back.
If we win, there's the
chance we could meet
with the king and explain
the situation to him.
But many more letters
of apology are inevitable.
I know, I know!
I just hope a nice letter
will be all it takes.
To be honest with you,
I lost count of all the times
I had to beg forgiveness.
Sometimes the letters
would stack up so high
they would fill the guild's
storehouse floor to ceiling.
And there were all
the invoices for damages,
the bills for reimbursemen,
cost estimates for repairs...
[MAKAROV] I'm glad I'm not alone
in this feeling, First Master.
[MAVIS] It's a big part
of the guild master's job.
Wow, you really know
about a lot of stuff,
Master Mavis!
I think you're cool!
Aw, that's sweet.
but grownups like me
know a lot of stuff!
You're shrimpy
for a grown up.
but you're still cool.
[MAVIS] Shrimpy?!
Now, be nice, darlin'.
Sorry, bout that.
We're still working on
learning our manners, right?
Oh. it's fine.
I'm not that upset.
Kids say the
darnedest things, huh?
I'm a grownup after all.
But I thought you were
a kid just like I am.
As a matter of fact,
I happen to be
the oldest person here...
Everybody's a kid to me.
I'm so grown-up, I'm
actually an apparition.
[ASCA] What does that word mean?
Uh... It's another way
of saying, 'spirit' or 'ghost.'
I still don't
understand what she is.
Me either, the whole
thing pretty much
goes over my head too.
If you're not a kid,
how come you're so tiny?
I'm much more than that!
Big things can come
in small packages...
Take Tenrou Island, for example!
Although it may seem
tiny to the untrained eye...
Both of our masters
are so weird...
she's manic and he's sleeping.
But, back
to the games.
It seems like the
match stalled out.
[ALZACK] Well,
the capital's huge
and there aren't
many competitors left.
[BISCA] The ones that are still
in it are super powerful, too...
I guess everyone's
kinda playing it safe.
Who knows who you might run
into coming around the corner?
[MILLIANNA] Looks like
the coast is clear...
Awesome.
I mean,
that's awesome.
What sucks is that Kagura
and I are the only ones
left on our whole team.
We're totally outnumbered.
What should I do now?
Maybe I should go
and try to look for her
so at least we can
have each other's back.
[CAT meows]
Ah!
[MILLIANNA] Mee-oww!
What a pretty kitty!
Come on, precious!
Here kitty, kitty!
Such a cutie-patootie.
Do you want
snuggles?
Come on and I'll give you
lots of snuggle-wuggles...
I'll rub your belly, and
scratch behind your widdle ears.
[LEADER] If you've made your
peace, it's time to die.
You must pay for
your transgressions.
[NATSU] I'm sick of this.
Let me pass before
this gets ugly.
[NATSU gasps]
Holy crap!
[LEADER] Why do
you run from me?!
What kinda
question is that?
[LEADER] For your crimes,
I must collect your head!
Man, you are
super scary.
[LEADER] I am the
hand of justice.
What's truly
frightening are criminals
who think they've done no wrong.
[NATSU] You're still
talking about that stuff?
Pop!
[PANTHERLILY grunts]
[NEPPA] Sploosh!
[NEPPA chuckles]
[NEPPA] What happened?
I thought you were
gonna cut me off?
Did ya get too scared?
[PANTHERLILY] Just how much
of a fool do you take me for?
I know I can't cut through acid.
And this here is some
extra powerful stuff.
It can turn that big 'ol sword.
into a big 'ol puddle o' goo.
[PANTHERLILY thinking]
Does he get his power
from whatever's in that bottle?
It's small, but it seems like
there's an endless supply of it.
The only way that I can
beat him is by getting in close.
But how do I do that?
[NEPPA] A pussycat puddle.
Hey! Runnin' and hidin'
ain't gonna help ya!
We don't need to be
here forever, ya know?
It's happy hour for me!
[PANTHERLILY shouting]
[NEPPA] So, ya wanna
play hide and seek?
Sploosh!
[PANTHERLILY] A true warrior
recognizes his limitations...
And takes the initiative
to get the upper hand!
[NEPPA] Nice try, kitty!
[NEPPA laughs,
PANTHERLILY pants]
[NEPPA] You can play all
the little games you want...
Not a single one of them is
gonna get you outta here alive!
There's more than
one way to skin a cat,
but I like doing it with acid!
[MIRAJANE grunting]
[KAMIKA] I remember
you now, they called you
Mirajane the "She-Devil".
You were once
a very powerful S-class
wizard, weren't you?
But looking at you now, I find
that extremely hard to believe.
So weak and emotional.
What happened to you?
Me? Well,
what about you?
The magic you that use is
so pretty and colorful...
Why do you use it
just to kill people?
[KAMIKA] What's this?
Are you trying to give me
some kind of lecture?
That's absolutely ridiculous
coming from a criminal.
But I'll tell you
what I'll do for you.
I'll give you the prettiest,
most colorful death.
I am Cosmos...
What about you, beautiful?
Will you tell me your name?
[WENDY] I'm Wendy Marvel.
[COSMOS] What a lovely name.
I will remember it fondly.
But, like I said,
you still must die...
Such is your fate.
That's what you think!
I'm a Fairy Tail wizard!
That means there's no
way you can beat me!
Or any of my friends!
[COSMOS] I'm a Hungry Wolf,
which means I will fulfill my
duty to the kingdom.
And you and your
friends will die.
What are those?!
No. Again with
the pickled plums?
[COSMOS] I'm so sorry
to disappoint you,
but they aren't pickled plums.
They are my special,
lovely magic fruit.
Now. eat up!
Oh? Do you think
that you're too sweet
to enjoy sour things? How sad.
[WENDY] Uh, no!
That's not true in the least.
In fact... I love them!
They're my favorite!
[COSMOS] Oh, Really? Mine, too!
The sensation they give
on the tongue is divine...
But my magic fruits
are extra special...
They're ten
times more sour.
Ten times?! I can
hardly even look at them!
[COSMOS] So amazingly sour!
The taste is to die for!
[WENDY screams]
[COSMOS] Oh, you
just have to try one!
Come on, eat up! Open wide!
[WENDY whimpers]
Terrain Effect Magic:
Lava Zone!
[ALL gasp]
This is not
gonna be good.
Yeah...
Watch out, Carla!
The ground is burning!
What do we do?
[ARCADIOS] Is it too late?
[LUCY whimpers]
Yukino! Lucy!
[LUCY grunts]
[YUKINO grunting]
[CARLA] There they
are! Over there!
Just hang on!
We're coming!
[HAPPY] We'll save you!
Nuh-uh!
[CARLA &amp; HAPPY scream]
He's gone fishing again!
But I'm not a fish,
I'm an Exceed!
Terrain Effect:
Gravity Zone!
[CARLA &amp; HAPPY grunting]
Oh no, they're
in trouble!
I feel like
I weigh a ton!
Me too.
It's a gravity
controlling spell.
[LUCY grunting]
[LUCY] Stay strong,
we can get through this!
[YUKINO] I know.
But I'm just afraid that this
rock is gonna crumble away!
He was right!
There ain't gonna be no
bones left when I'm done!
[ARCADIOS] No. I have
to do something!
[LUCY yelps]
[YUKINO grunts]
[ARCADIOS] I can't let you die!
The fate of the world
is counting on you!
For the Eclipse!
I'm sorry, Arcadios.
Are you crazy?! Why are
you still talking about that?!
I already told you I wasn't
gonna be any part of it!
[ARCADIOS] The Eclipse
will save the world.
You are the keys
to its success.
My life is not as important!
[YUKINO gasps]
[ARCADIOS] I'm willing
to sacrifice myself...
to save you!
No, please!
[LUCY] Wait! What
in the heck are you doing?!
[ARCADIOS groaning]
[screaming]
[HAPPY] This is horrible!
We gotta do somethin'
or else Lucy and Yukino
are gonna get burned up!
[NATSU] They've got all those
cosmic animal spirits and stuff
that can save them, right?
[HAPPY] It seems you've
forgotten that they need
their keys to summon spirits
and they don't
have 'em right now!
[NATSU] Well, I think
you've forgotten that
Lucy's got a special spirit
that can come and go
whenever he feels like it...
[HAPPY] Oh yeah, you're right!
I totally forgot
all about that one.
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time:
Scorching Earth!
[HAPPY] Yeah, he can
take care of everything.
They'll be okay.
[NATSU] Yep, and we can focus on
gettin' out and gettin' payback!