It's you.
You're that Black Wizard.
Wait. What the hell are
you doing with Mavis?
What's going on?
Is she okay?
Where did you find her?
No one has seen or heard
from her for a year now.
We've all been sick with worry.
[ZEREF] Tell me, are you
the only person here?
Now? Yes.
Everyone's getting ready
for the harvest festival.
Due to Mavis' absence,
I've been obliged to serve as
Fairy Tail's temporary Master.
[ZEREF]
Master?
Oh, right. I'd completely
forgotten this was a guild.
I have come here to
return Mavis to you.
Hey! What the--?!
You can't throw her
around like that!
She's not a doll, you know!
Don't worry. Nothing
can hurt her anymore.
[PRECHT]
Hey! Mavis!
Are you okay? Answer me!
What happened to you?
It's like she's
in a deep sleep.
Yes. And she will
never wake from it.
[gasps]
[ZEREF]
Sweet dreams. Mavis.
Who are you? What's your name?
[ZEREF]
Zeref.
[gasps]
[ZEREF] In essence, Mavis was
a fairy, but I am a spriggan.
A being most grotesque
and monstrous.
[ZEREF]
I'm so exhausted.
These feelings have
left me drained.
All I want is numb seclusion.
I know.
I'll go back to Alakitasia and
play my game some more.
There's no one I care about
on that entire continent.
[ZEREF] Trying to love
someone was a mistake.
It was wrong.
I must harden my
heart once again.
[gasps] Zeref? No.
He's the legendary Black
Wizard? That can't be.
[PRECHT]
Mavis, please, open your eyes.
What in the hell
is wrong with you?
Is it true? Is she dead?
[PRECHT] Strange.
I can't sense a heartbeat.
She's not alive,
but there is a residual
magic power inside her.
I must resuscitate her at once.
As I recall, there's
a revival lacrima
in a chamber beneath
the guild hall.
[MAVIS]
And so,
that's how my body ended
up inside the lacrima.
And why it remains there today.
Precht worked tirelessly,
trying every resurrection
spell he could find,
but not a single one could
bring me back to life.
One day, because of his
vast knowledge of magic,
he finally realized
what had happened.
I had been stricken by
the Curse of Ankhselam.
[PRECHT]
Oh, god.
Was this curse what
caused Rita's death?
[PRECHT] No. I can't let
anybody else find out.
The guild would not survive.
[MAVIS]
He kept his word.
No one would know
the truth about me.
[MAVIS]
In 697, Precht made up his mind.
He decided to tell the guild
that I'd passed away.
A shrine over an empty grave
was erected on Tenrou Island,
which was declared
our sacred land.
That is where I was born.
And where I met my fellow
founders of the guild:
Precht, Warrod, and Yuri.
[MAVIS]
That same year,
Precht became Fairy
Tail's second master.
He was acting in accordance
to the wish I had made known
in the time before
my disappearance.
He devoted all his time not
spent performing his duties
as guild master in solitude,
working without
rest to revive me.
In the year 700, Makarov's
father, Yuri Dreyer,
died prematurely,
never knowing the true
cause of his wife's death.
Precht continued his
attempts to resurrect me
for the next 30 years.
Though not successful,
the results yielded something
rather unexpected.
As I'd said, he had vast
knowledge about magic
and exhausted his resources
to bring me back,
but I remained in suspended
animation inside the lacrima,
unable to age or truly die.
In an unforeseen
convergence of factors,
an inexplicable form
of magic was created.
[MAVIS] It was something
that would rock
the wizarding world
to its very core.
Eternal magic...
called Fairy Heart.
[BOTH gasp]
I don't understand. What is it?
Yes, please. Elaborate.
An everlasting source of magic.
Simply put,
the power that springs from
Fairy Heart will never dry up.
Are you serious?
Like magic you can keep
using forever and ever?
[MAVIS]
Consider the weapon developed
by the old Magic Council,
the Etherion Cannon.
It was powerful enough to
wipe out an entire country
with one blast.
The Fairy Heart contains
enough magic energy
to fire an infinite number
of Etherion blasts.
Or perhaps, "contains" is
not the right word for it.
It can "generate" that
kind of magic energy.
Enough to wipe out
all countries.
I understand why we'd
wanna keep this a secret.
News like this would definitely
throw the wizarding world
into total chaos.
Ivan tried to get his hands
on it some years ago.
It seems word of its existence
has reached the shores
of Alvarez as well.
Which means they're
gonna launch an invasion
to try to take control of
the power it can generate.
But why would they go
through the trouble?
Aren't they already swimming
in magic power over there?
Well, my theory is that they
wanna use it as a weapon
in the fight against Acnologia.
Even Zeref considers him to
be too evil for this world.
Is he really that strong?
I mean, I know he's
like a force of nature,
but that's insane.
It's so scary.
[grunts]
Wait a sec.
This might seem like a stupid
question to you guys,
but if we have something
that's this powerful,
what's stopping us from
usin' it on both of them?
Boom! Yeah! Take that,
you baddies! Boom!
I suppose that question
needs to be asked.
I must admit, I did consider
using it to stop the Faces
in the battle with Tartaros.
Although we would've clinched
a short-term victory,
there was no telling what
the long-lasting effects
might've been.
For example,
what if we'd lost control
of the Etherion
and it rained down
limitless destruction?
[screams]
Jeez, sorry for asking.
Remember, you can't
counteract a poison
with another poison, Happy.
Be careful. I'm not sure she
enjoys being called a poison.
No matter what we're up against,
Fairy Heart must remain secret.
The world just
isn't ready for it.
[MEMBER A] Yeah! There's
no way we'd give that up!
[MEMBER C]
It's your body!
We're gonna protect you with
everything in our power!
[gasps]
I never dreamed my sin
would cause all this.
I dragged my beloved Fairy Tail
into a mess that could
end us for good.
[GAJEEL]
What "sin"?
Huh?
Because opening up your
heart to love someone
isn't actually a sin in my book.
And if it was illegal...
I wouldn't arrest ya.
[chuckles]
Stop with the blank
stares, would ya?!
He's right.
And you mustn't blame
yourself for what's happened.
[gasps]
It's unfortunate,
but it's obviously not
what you had intended.
Because of you, Fairy Tail is
a force for good in the world.
And no Fairy Tail...
...would mean that we wouldn't
all be friends today.
I'd be sad!
You made this happen.
Your love for people is what
brought us all together.
And we're willing to
do whatever it takes
to protect the guild
you created,
because we believe in it.
Your guild's grown into a thing
of beauty, First Master.
[GRAY]
Ah!
It's hard to imagine something
so tragic and painful
as being forced to fight the
person you once madly loved.
The feelings I had for him
are long in the past.
Zeref is a threat. To Ishgar
and all of humanity.
He must be defeated!
Not gonna lie. It'll be tough.
Even if we took down
Alvarez's army...
Zeref himself can't age
or die, isn't that right?
[MEMBER B]
Wait, he's really immortal?
[MEMBER D]
You mean, like,
there's nothing
that can kill him?
How do we defeat
somebody like that?
[NATSU laughing]
Just leave that part
to me, you guys!
I'll be the one to
take down Zeref.
Because my right arm...
is a secret weapon, too.
Hey, have I told you lately
that you're the epitome
of triple A-plus beauty?
[MARIN yelps]
I'd be even better if you
finished this pedicure.
[MARIN]
Of course, my lady!
I will put all of my care into
making these nails truly divine.
When I'm done, they'll
be the envy of the gods!
So, my lady, if it's
not asking too much,
do you think you'd be
willing to turn me
back to my normal size,
pretty please?
--[door opens]
--[MARIN] Hm?
Tell me, Randi.
Yeah, Mary?
I heard you let some
troublemakers escape.
Surely that's not true.
No, I did not let them "escape."
I wasn't in the mood to be
dealing with them is all.
[MARIN] Trust me,
I tried to convince her
that it wasn't the best idea!
Oh, my. You are looking
A-plus too, my lady!
Would you turn him
back to normal?
He's like a disgusting
cockroach that can talk.
[MARIN]
Say what?!
I'll pass.
[MARIN]
Come on! I hate being tiny!
Are you ever in the mood
to deal with anything?
That's what he's for, right?
Anyway, the Spriggan Twelve
have been summoned.
Your lackey's magic
should spare you
the hassle of traveling.
[door slams]
[MARIN yelps]
[MARIN grunts]
[MARIN] Hey, be careful!
What are you doing?
I can't stand that cow.
So horrible and ugly.
If I were you, I'd say
she's an F-minus.
Please don't squash me.
So...
Tell us more about
this "secret weapon."
Well, it's a secret.
[LUCY]
What?!
That's why it's a secret weapon!
Just tell us what it is,
you pink-haired punk!
How the hell can your right
arm be a secret anyway?
You know, I don't have a
clue what's under there,
but knowing him, I'll bet
it's something super special.
[HAPPY humming]
Are you acting smug
because you're in on
what the "secret
weapon" really is?
I don't know!
Well, I don't know
why you feel the need
to be so showy about it
when it's not even your
own secret to be hiding.
All I can say is that it's
a one-time-use technique.
With this, I'll be able to take
down ol' Zeref once and for all.
There's no way I'm
gonna lose to him.
[MEMBER G]
Whoa!
[FAIRY TAIL chattering]
[MEMBER E]
Only one time?
[MEMBER F] He's literally
got an ace up his sleeve!
[NATSU]
You know it!
Well, he makes a pretty
convincing argument,
doesn't he?
Yes, indeed.
And his confidence seems to
be quite contagious as well.
Leave the firing up to Natsu!
He certainly does know
how to boost our morale!
Aye, sir!
[LAXUS]
Hmph.
He's always had a
knack for this stuff.
Of course, I have several
strategies of my own,
but I'll let Natsu lead for now.
Master.
[ERZA, MAKAROV, MAVIS]
Go on.
[LUCY]
Uhh. I guess I mean Gramps.
You should probably tell
us everything you know
about who we're
going up against.
[grunts] Yes,
that's a good point.
I'll share what information
I was able to glean
in my time there.
At the top sits
Emperor Spriggan.
Here in Ishgar, he's more
commonly referred to
as the legendary
"Black Wizard Zeref."
[grunts]
And beneath him are
powerful wizards.
An elite and terrifyingly
ruthless force
known as the Spriggan Twelve.
During the year I was
confined there,
I only managed to
meet six of them.
And because it's such
a large region,
it's apparently quite
rare for all of them
to be in the same place
at the same time.
Seven of you.
I'm pleased that so
many made it here
despite the sudden notice.
Actually, I believe Neinhart
is lurking somewhere
inside the palace, Your Majesty.
But well...
It's quite all right.
[INVEL]
I respectfully disagree.
Not attending this meeting
is an unacceptable defiance
of Your Majesty's orders.
[MAKAROV] Invel,
A.K.A. the Winter General.
Zeref's right hand man.
And his chief administrator.
I'm not sure, but his
nickname leads me to believe
that he utilizes
ice-based magic,
though I haven't
seen him in action.
Ice, huh?
[AJEEL] Don't be such a
stick in the mud, Invel.
There's more than enough of
us here to start the meeting.
I think a small force
would be nicer anyway.
[MAKAROV]
Ajeel, the Desert King.
He's the sand wizard
we encountered
during our escape from Alvarez.
As we experienced,
he's one of the Twelve's
most aggressive members.
He couldn't stop us.
[ZEREF] As I'm sure
you've likely surmised,
I've convened this meeting
to discuss preparations
for our invasion of Ishgar.
What a hassle.
Now, now, you really shouldn't
say such things, Brandish.
Don't forget, you did agree
to follow my orders.
Yes, of course.
I didn't actually say
I wasn't going to do it.
Just that it sounded like a
massive pain in the neck to me.
[MAKAROV] Brandish,
the Nation Destroyer.
Though not much of a hawk,
she does wield
enough magic power
to wipe countries off the map.
[ERZA] We have encountered her
before, on Caracol Island.
She's a force to
be reckoned with.
From what I could tell,
her magic can alter
an object's mass.
You know, Randi,
the fact that you say
whatever's on your mind
is why everyone hates you.
Yeah, so what?
I don't really give a damn
because the truth is,
I actually hate them.
I see.
Then I guess it's no wonder
we get along so well.
[MAKAROV]
Dimaria, the Warrior Queen.
I don't know what
magic she uses,
but she's an extremely
skilled knight
who's touted as a goddess
of the battlefield.
So she's a wizard and a knight?
Sounds kinda familiar,
doesn't it?
Tell us, God Serena,
will destroying your
homeland cause you pain?
Painful?
No!
Jackass.
But thank you.
[MAKAROV] God Serena,
the top-ranked ex-member
of the Ten Wizard Saints.
He's a profound disappointment
to our country,
and impossible to like,
but I've had the
chance to witness
his extraordinary magic
power firsthand.
I still can't even wrap
my head around the fact
that the highest-ranked
Wizard Saint
is working with the enemy now.
I wonder why he decided
to desert Ishgar.
Honestly, I highly doubt that
there's any way to know for sure
without asking him personally.
I'll make sure to do that...
when I arrest him.
Your Majesty, there's
no doubt in my mind
that we are prepared
to go to battle
in this final war of Ragnarok.
[MAKAROV]
August, the Wizard King.
Be especially wary of him.
Although I don't know much
about him personally,
his magic power is rumored
to be without equal
among the Twelve.
He's on a completely
different level.
[MAKAROV]
If what I've heard is true,
he's mastered all
manner of magic
from every corner of the world.
It has been said that
he might even wield
more types of magic
than Zeref himself.
[gasps]
That's all the information
I have on those six.
As far as the others, I only
have the names of three.
They're...
...Bloodman...
...Neinhart...
...and the last one is Wall.
As I understand it,
our target is the body of
your former love interest.
It's all very scandalous
and sinful indeed.
[ZEREF]
Then you misunderstand.
The Fairy Heart is a form
of magic, not a person.
Additionally, that is not
our mission's only goal.
We will also wipe out Ishgar.
Humanity must be
exterminated without fail.
Humanity? Well.
We are but pieces in this game.
A fascinating
interpretation indeed.
[BRANDISH]
Hm.
Yes, good.
On that note, let's
plan our strategy.
[AJEEL]
Hm. I got it!
You should let me
do it all by myself!
We'll need to formulate
our strategy.
Everybody, pay close attention.
I'm sorry. But I simply
cannot allow that.
This will be a
full-scale assault.
Zeref will invade Ishgar
with his entire army.
Come on! I can handle the
whole thing on my own!
If the strongest guy
there was God Serena,
then that means
I'll have no problem
taking on the whole
continent alone!
[YAJEEL]
Hmm...
[ZEREF] I agree with what
you're saying, Ajeel.
But still, I like the message
an all-out attack sends.
There's not a shred
of ambiguity.
[MAVIS]
I won't sugar coat it.
There's no question we are at
an overwhelming disadvantage.
Our enemy is greater in number
and far more powerful than
any we've faced before.
[ZEREF]
The Dragon King Festival begins.
Let the invasion commence.
But due to our courage and
our bond, we will prevail.
Let's show them what
our guild is made of!
[chuckles]
[FAIRY TAIL cheering]
My arm is aching.
The same one that was devoured
by the Flame Dragon.
This is my time.
The Dragon King Festival
will soon begin.
[growls]
Behold and tremble before
the true King of Dragons,
the ultimate life form
on this planet...
...Acnologia!
[LUCY] Everybody in the
guild has their own way
of making it through
the stressful night
before the battle for
our future begins.
And things quickly get intense
when Alvarez's massive army
comes shooting through
the sky towards Fiore!
Humanity is counting
on us to fend them off.
As the town of Magnolia
comes under attack,
our guild's strong
bonds of solidarity
are put to the ultimate test.
Next Time: "The Magnolia
Defensive War."
Waves of threats and
despair come crashing in,
but we won't fall!