[NARRATOR] The town of Magnolia,
in the year seven-ninety-one.
[LUCY] After all the craziness
on Tenrou Island had passed,
we learned that seven years
had passed along with it.
I guess time flies when
you're saving the world.
It's like something
out of a book.
I never imagined I'd experience
anything like it firsthand,
but I guess that's
part of the job.
I've made some incredible
memories since I joined
Fairy Tail but I don't think
I will ever forget that night.
We jam packed seven
years' worth of drinking,
dancing, and singing
into one party.
It sure is good
to be home again.
♪
I see you're rocking
fire magic too, Romeo!
Watch out world, it's
getting' hot up in here!
Look, I can even
make cold flames!
[PANTHERLILY]
That is quite 'cool'.
And what is this one?
It's a purple flame
that can stick to anything
it's cast on.
And I got this funky yellow one
that smells like dragon farts.
Pee-yew!
You have a
strange gift.
If you ask me, you've already
outclassed your old man.
Hold up, I've smelled
that fire before.
Aye.
Don't tell my dad,
but I've secretly been
taking magic lessons
from Master Totomaru!
Get out!
I didn't know he was teaching!
[PANTHERLILY]
This is rare.
It's nice to see
a smile on his face.
[NATSU] Man, that
sure takes me back.
I still need to taste the
rest of his colored flames.
Sweet!
Fire buffet,
here I come!
[ROMEO] Sorry,
but I don't think he's
too keen on seeing you, Natsu.
Wow, shocker.
I gotta admit Macao,
I certainly didn't expect
you'd be willing
to wear the big shoes.
Well, they never
quite fit me.
Let's just say that I was
keepin' 'em warm for you.
Now that you're back
I can enjoy a stiff drink.
Oh?
And here I was thinkin' about
letting you keep the position.
Are you serious?
[NARRATOR] First Master: Mavis.
Second Master: Precht.
Third Master: Makarov.
And Fourth Master:
Macao Conbolt.
Maybe I could
drink and be Master!
Dunno if this is
the best decision
you've made but I think
it's kinda funny.
Me too.
You're married?
Co-Congratulations!
Wh-When did
this happen?
About six
years ago.
Sure wish all you
guys coulda' been there.
Poor thing nearly
passed out when I proposed.
It was adorable.
[ALZACK] Did ya have
to bring that up?
No!
How could you get
married without me there!
Would someone stop her?
Looks like Erza
blew a fuse.
I can't say
I blame her,
I'm bummed I couldn't
be there, too.
That's wonderful!
Do you have children?
We have a daughter.
Yeah, we named
her Asca.
Reedus, is this
what I think it is?
Oui!
I tried to imagine what
you would've looked like
seven years older and that
drawing was the end result!
[WENDY] My chest.
[REEDUS] Hmm?
Is there a problem?
[CARLA] Oh, my,
this is horrifying.
[PANTHERLILY] Why am
I wearing a loincloth?
You know, we were gone
for a really long time.
I wonder if the other Exceeds
ever got worried about us.
[PANTHERLILY]
Doubtful.
Exceeds have a different
sense of time than humans.
I find it highly
unlikely that our absence
was even noticed.
[HAPPY] Oh yeah?
[CARLA] I suppose
that's comforting.
[WENDY] This isn't fair.
Why does reality keep
crushing my dreams like this?
Huh?
Is there something
wrong with the picture?
[REEDUS]
I liked it.
I must say, Kinana,
it looks like
the past seven years
have treated you well.
That's so
sweet of you.
Thank you, Master.
So, tell me, have any of
your memories come back yet?
No, nothing so far.
I wonder why.
Although, there
have been times when
I can hear somebody
calling to me.
[KINANA] "Let me hear
your voice," they say.
And sometimes,
I feel as if I know them.
They're so
familiar and gentle.
[door opens]
[KINANA] Welcome!
May I help you?
[MAN] Wonderful.
It seems the rumors were true!
Who are these bozos?
I think I know.
Hello my lovelies!
I'm glad to hear your
deaths were exaggerated.
You appear to be
in great health!
The sentiment's a little
redundant when they haven't aged
in seven years.
[LYON] You've barely been back
two days and you've already
trashed the place.
No way.
Whoa, it's
Lamia Scale!
Blue Pegasus and Lamia
Scale helped us search
for Tenrou Island longer
than anyone else would.
[ERZA] We appreciate it.
[GRAY] Well I guess
we owe you one, man.
I'd love to take you
up on that, but I've got
seven years on you now.
And I'm not the kinda guy
who takes advantage of children.
Yeah, rub it in!
So you see, things haven't
been completely bad
while you guys were taking
your seven year siesta.
In that time,
Lamia Scale climbed the ranks
to Fiore's second best guild!
No hard feelings.
Right, Lucy?
Second, huh?
[LUCY]
Is Pegasus number one?
Oh yeah, real funny!
Those lame wads!
Here we go.
Toby.
You're embarrassing
yourself again.
Now,
Toby's wild rant aside,
we're just glad
to have you back with us.
That's right!
My god.
I never believed in
true love until now.
[LUCY] Whoa!
I don't think
he's playin' around!
[GRAY] He has no idea what
he's gettin' himself into here!
No.
The love triangle
has become a...
Love maze!
What a healthy
imagination.
It's anything
but "healthy."
So, anyway...
Guess which lucky guy
just found out he's a daddy!
Hold up!
You're bein' too touchy-feely.
Come on, give
Papa some kisses!
You're embarrassing me!
[arguing]
Do they seriously think
they're fooling anyone
with that act?
Just go along
with it;
I mean, it's awkward
enough as it is.
[ALZACK] Here she is!
My precious baby girl!
She definitely
takes after you two.
[PANTHERLILY]
I agree!
She kind of reminds me
of Wendy in a way.
Tiny and adorable.
[GAJEEL] Yeah.
--[WENDY] Stop picking on me!
--[PANTHERLILY] Huh?
[PANTHERLILY]
What'd I say?
[LUCY] The excitement
never ends.
For those of us on Tenrou
Island, only a week had passed.
But for our friends
and family, a long and lonely
stretch of suffering had
finally come to an end.
When I think about
what they went through,
I can't help but feel a strange
sense of guilt for their pain.
That's a long time to wait.
[HAPPY] The Seven Year Gap!
[LUCY] Oh man, I cannot wait
to soak in my own bath again!
[MAN A] Is that Lucy?
[MAN B] Whoa, it couldn't be.
Crap.
It's the landlady.
[LANDLADY] I heard you
were back, Miss Heartfilia.
I hope you and your
pocket book are in good health
'cause you owe me
seven years rent.
Five million, eight-hundred
and eighty-eight
thousand jewel.
I'm not letting you
inside your apartment
until I've been paid in full.
[LUCY] Five million,
eight-hundred eighty-eight
thousand jewel.
How am I supposed
to get that kind of cash?
I can't go
to the guild for help.
That was all the money I had.
We'll just consider the
rest of it a debt, okay?
[LUCY] The girls staying
in Fairy Hills had to pay
seven years of back rent, too.
I guess we'll all
be broke together.
Seven years.
We missed out on
so many important things.
Romeo's grown into
a handsome young wizard.
Jet and Droy have
gotten older and wider.
Bisca and Alzack are
raising the next generation
of the guild.
And on top of that,
everyone else is recovering
from Gildart's and
Cana's bombshell.
Makes me think about my dad.
Poor guy.
It's been seven years since
he's heard anything from me.
He must be worried sick.
Maybe it's time
I paid my old man a visit.
You know, Plue.
This might be the first time
I've actually missed my dad.
Pretty silly, isn't it?
But don't think I'm going
to see him to ask for money!
'Cause I'm not!
[LUCY] Still, those seven
years we lost weighed heavily
on the hearts of
the Tenrou Island team.
[BISCA] Erza.
I thought you'd
like to know about
Jellal.
Hold on now.
[JURA] By the way, Makarov, the
Wizard Saints will be holding
a meeting very soon.
You should come.
You need to be debriefed,
and there's a matter
of importance to discuss.
You know Ultear and a girl
named Meldy, don't you?
Yeah, but how do you
know about those two?
[NATSU] Gone!
It's gone!
[HAPPY] It can't be!
Tear the place apart
if you have to!
[NATSU] If we don't
find it, we're screwed!
[MAKAROV] So you're still
alive after all, Zeref.
Carriages are
death traps.
I'm never riding
one again.
You say that
every time, Natsu.
Question...
Why did you guys have
to tag along with me?
Cause our piggybanks are
full of moths right now!
We thought
Daddy Lucy might know
a 'get-fish-quick scheme'
that'll save our tushies!
[LUCY] It's called a
"get-rich-quick" scheme,
and I don't understand
why you even need one.
Last time I checked
you didn't rent a house!
Our stupid safe
ran off while we were stuck
on Tenrou Island!
And it took all of our
food funds with it!
How are we supposed
to eat now!
[NARRATOR] The prosperous
merchant guild, Love and Lucky.
[LUCY] Excuse me,
may I ask you something?
Yes, ma'am?
Do you happen to know
if Mr. Jude Heartfilia
will be coming in today?
He's still registered
here, isn't he?
Would you be Jude's
daughter by any chance?
[LUCY] Yep!
There a problem,
lady?
Is he out
sick today?
Do you have
his home address?
[RECEPTIONIST] Um...
Actually...
I'm very sorry to have
to tell you this, but...
Jude passed away
a little over a month ago.
It was a shock to all of us.
[LUCY] The weight of those
seven years keeps piling on.
[HAPPY] Lucy, I--
[NATSU] Happy.
[GIRL A]
So, like, my old man
is like so freakin'
annoying, right?
Yeah and my
daddy's, like,
mega-irritating, y'know?
And he smells.
[GIRL A] He's totes
stinky, like, whoa!
[GIRL B] Like whoa
and half, right?
Wouldn't it be
great if they just,
like, dropped dead?
[GIRL B] That would be
totes brill, girlfriend!
What's the
matter with you?
Are you loudmouths
really that dense?
Read the mood!
[GIRL B]
Wow, rude much?
[GIRL A] For real.
Like, who even
cares about reading?
Shut up!
Just get lost,
would ya?
Yeah scram!
We already
were leaving.
By the way,
your dog stinks.
[GIRL B] Talk about
a total creepazoid.
[LUCY] Cut it out.
Uh...
Okay.
[LUCY] I'm sorry for putting
you through all this trouble.
[HAPPY] Are you
gonna be okay, Lucy?
[LUCY] Yeah.
I'm just shocked
about my dad, is all.
I'll be just fine.
[LUCY] I know a few years
have passed but it feels like
I saw him alive and
healthy a couple months ago.
It's hard to accept that
I'll never get to see or speak
to him again.
It's weird.
When I think back, I never
really got along with my Dad
when I was growing up.
And the thing
with Phantom certainly
didn't help matters.
But then,
after what
happened in Acalypha,
I truly felt like my
relationship with him
had been changed
for the better.
[LUCY] It's just like him
to work himself sick.
Guess it was
too much this time.
What bothers me most
is that even though I feel sad
and I miss him...
I can't cry.
The tears just aren't there.
Does that mean, in the end,
he meant nothing to me?
[NATSU] No of
course it doesn't.
I dunno how to explain it.
But I don't think whether
you cry or not means you cared
any less about him.
[LUCY] Thanks, Natsu.
You're right.
I know that.
I already feel better.
[NARRATOR] The wizard guild,
Twilight Ogre.
[BANABOSTER] I'm done
playin' games, old man.
I ain't got nothin' else
to say to you, mmkay?
There ain't no way
I'm gonna back down
until you and your guild have
paid the debt you owe me.
[NARRATOR] This is
Twilight Ogre's master,
Banaboster.
I would like nothing
more than to pay you.
But, I'm sure you're well
aware of the financial rut
we've found ourselves in.
Your business records
have a lot of holes in them.
It makes ya wonder if we're
paying more than we really owe.
Would you care
to explain that?
You tramp!
Are you accusin' me
of fraud or somethin'?
[MAKAROV] Not at all!
You can be assured that
we'll repay whatever we owe
with proper interest.
Someday.
You're startin'
to try my patience,
you little piss-ant!
Forgive me,
that came out wrong.
What I meant is that we
should start by renegotiating
our interest rate.
What!
I don't negotiate with dead
beats who rough up my boys
and don't pay their debts.
Capiche?
You think you're tough,
little man,
but I'll make you pay
for bein' disrespectful!
Me and my boys got
a reputation to uphold!
Understood.
We only came here
to discuss money,
but we can discuss
your reputation as well.
I have no problem
telling you what I think.
You wanna wear cement
shoes, ya old geezer!
"Get payback
for what's owed."
If memory serves,
that's the Twilight Ogre creed.
Much like
"an eye for an eye."
[ERZA] Indeed.
And when you think of it
in those terms, you owe us
for seven years of
property damage and abuse.
[MIRAJANE] So it
seems you owe us.
It's only fair our guild
be paid back for each
and every claim
during that time.
[MAKAROV] The suffering my
children endured at your hands,
all the years
I wasn't there for them.
It brings tears to my eyes.
You hear me?
So if it's war you want,
then it's war you're gonna get!
[MACAO] Good grief.
Well, I never really
expected them to go
the diplomatic route
in the first place.
I'm surprised that
they held out this long.
You know.
Hearing them go to work in
there makes the past seven years
seem like nothin'
more than a bad dream.
I couldn't agree more.
[WAKABA] Natsu!
Happy!
What are you doin' here?
[MACAO] I thought you guys
went to Acalypha with Lucy?
Are you gonna join the brawl?
[WAKABA] Don't!
The last thing we need
is a fireball on our hands!
[WAKABA] What's up with them?
[MACAO] Beats me.
Tsoo-wee.
Tsoo-wee!
[FATHER] Hey pumpkin!
[LITTLE GIRL] Daddy!
[LUCY] The landlady?
[LUCY] Hey!
What're you-
Help!
Someone!
I'm way too pretty to die!
[LUCY] My apartment.
But, it looks exactly the
way I left it seven years ago.
[LANDLADY] I've been
cleaning it every week.
Other than a few
of your outfits,
everything held up
pretty well over the years.
I even salvaged
some of them.
I left all your mail
on the table there.
Without fail, they
would show up every year
on the same day.
[JUDE'S VOICE] To my
dearest daughter, Lucy,
happy birthday.
From Papa.
[LUCY] He remembered?
[LANDLADY] Oh yeah.
The one on your bed
arrived this morning.
[JUDE'S VOICE] My dearest Lucy,
happy birthday.
As I write this letter,
I find myself wondering
when you'll get to read it.
A long time has
passed since the news of
your disappearance reached me.
I'm very worried, but
I have faith that you're safe.
You're so much
like your mother:
Stubborn as a rock
and blessed with luck.
I'm sure you're fine and
that I'll see you again someday.
As for me, business
is booming, and I'm about
to close a big deal
with the western region.
It keeps me busy, but I'm
still living a fulfilling life.
I think of you and Layla
every single day.
Those memories keep me going.
I miss you terribly.
Wherever you are, I hope you're
living life to the fullest
and following your own path.
Please,
never forget how
proud I am of you.
[LUCY] I won't, Dad.
[JUDE'S VOICE] Lucy...
I love you.
That is one thing
that will never change.
Bye Daddy.
I love you, too.
Wow.
You really let
yourself go!
Did you eat an old lady
and steal her looks
for good measure?!
You can quit
your gawkin'.
I'm Lucy's
landlady.
I knew that.
Sooo, can
we come inside?
It'd be best if you
left her alone for now.
[NATSU] But--
[HAPPY] We got a job we think
she'd be interested in!
[LANDLADY] She doesn't
need to worry about work.
A letter came this morning
with seven years' worth of rent.
Honestly.
It's amazing what
some parents will do
to support their children.
For real!?
That means we're
the only ones who
still have to worry
about missing money!
[NATSU] We don't
have time to stand around!
Let's get to work!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
[NATSU] Yo, Lucy!
Me and Happy
are goin' on a job!
We'll pick up some white
clover dumplings for you
on the way back, okay?
[LUCY] The past seven years
may have left a painful mark
on every member of Fairy Tail...
[door opens]
[LUCY] Wait up!
I'll go with you!
[LUCY] ...but that's okay.
'Cause we're gonna keep living
this life to the fullest.
♪
[NATSU] There's
gonna be a magic ball?
I wonder what kind of
fancy food they'll have!
[HAPPY] Like
you'd ever get to go!
It's for mature,
sophisticated grown-ups only.
[NATSU] I bet there'll
be cheese balls, and cakes,
and venison, oh my!
Get in my belly!
[HAPPY] You're such a child.
I, on the other hand, am a
mature gentleman who will dance
the night away
with the lovely Carla.
[NATSU] In your dreams.
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next time: The Magic Ball!
[HAPPY] You should
never underestimate
Lord Baron Von Happy!
[NATSU] Wow, you've never been
that self-confident before.
[HAPPY] Yes, I have!
At least, I think so.