- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL...."
- Lucy: THAT REPORTER
FROM "SORCERER WEEKLY"
WAS SOMETHING ELSE, WASN'T HE?
- Happy: HE CERTAINLY DIDN'T
WANT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH YOU, LUCY.
- Lucy: DON'T LAUGH.
OF COURSE I'M GLAD
THINGS ARE FINALLY
SETTLING DOWN AROUND HERE.
- Natsu: YOU THINK?
EVERYTHING SEEMS THE SAME TO ME.
- Happy: ESPECIALLY ON THE
LUCY-HAVING-NO-BOYFRIEND FRONT.
- Lucy: JUST DROP IT, OKAY?!
- (theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( thunder rolls )
- Narrator: DARK AND RAINY DAYS
SUCH AS TODAY
ARE THANKFULLY
A RARITY IN MAGNOLIA.
BUT IN A PERPETUALLY DARK
AND GLOOMY PART OF TOWN,
THERE STANDS A DISREPUTABLE
POTION SHOP.
- DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
- OH? YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING
THAT'LL MAKE
A BOY NOTICE YOU?
MY CONCOCTIONS CAN'T BE TAILORED
TO SUCH SPECIFIC NEEDS.
- PLEASE, SIR.
IF HE WOULD GAZE AT ME
WITH PASSIONATE EYES JUST ONCE,
EVEN THAT WOULD BE ENOUGH.
- WELL, I DO HAVE SOMETHING
THAT MIGHT DO THE TRICK.
TRY THIS.  IT'LL DO
EXACTLY WHAT YOU'VE ASKED.
- WHAT IS IT?
- THIS WOULD ENSURE YOUR MAN
BURNS WITH A DESIRE
ONLY FOR YOU.
60,000 JEWEL.
- SEEMS RATHER PRICEY.
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO HAGGLE, YOUNG LADY.
DID I MENTION
IT'S 100% EFFECTIVE?
- 100%? BURNING WITH DESIRE?
I'LL TAKE
THE WHOLE BOTTLE, SIR.
DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
- Narrator:
NO ONE KNEW AT THE TIME,
BUT THE SUSPICIOUS POTION
JUVIA PURCHASED
ON THAT RARE RAINY DAY
AT FULL PRICE
WITHOUT ANY KIND
OF NEGOTIATION WHATSOEVER
WOULD BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR BRINGING FAIRY TAIL
TO THE VERY BRINK
OF DESTRUCTION.
- ( Happy speaking )
- UGH, I'M SO BORED.
- HOW ABOUT CHECKING
THE BOARD FOR A NEW JOB?
- I'D LIKE TO,
BUT NATSU KEEPS SAYING
THAT HE NEEDS TO TAKE
A LITTLE TIME OFF.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GO ON ONE BY YOURSELF?
OR MAYBE TEAM UP WITH
SOMEBODY DIFFERENT?
- HMM, IT'D BE TOO WEIRD
WORKING WITH ANYONE ELSE.
WE'RE A TEAM.
WE SHOULD STICK TOGETHER.
- YOU TWO ARE SO LOYAL
TO ONE ANOTHER.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
YOU'RE A COUPLE.
- UGH! IT'S SO NOT LIKE THAT!
- WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
DEEP DOWN, NATSU MIGHT
HAVE FEELINGS FOR YOU.
- UH...
- ( laughs )
- NA, NA, NA.
NA, NA, NA, NA, NA.
- YEAH, EVEN IF
THAT WERE THE CASE,
I'M AFRAID I WOULD
HAVE TO PASS.
- I THINK YOU TWO
WOULD BE ADORABLE TOGETHER.
- ( laughing )
- NA, NA, NA, NA...
- COME ON, NATSU,
QUIT GOOFING AROUND
AND LET'S GET
BACK TO WORK!
- WOULD YOU PUT SOME
CLOTHES ON ALREADY?!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
DID YOUR POWERS FINALLY
BURN THAT BRAIN OF YOURS
INTO A LUMP OF CHARCOAL?
- HEY, DON'T BE SUCH A KILLJOY.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO TAKE A BREAK
NOW AND THEN.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, HAPPY?
- ( humming )
AYE, SIR.  THIS SURE
FEELS GREAT.
- AND NOW THE FINALE.
- Both:
CHICKA, CHICKA, CHICKA!
- DEFINITELY A PASS.
- BUT I THINK
THE TWO OF YOU
WOULD MAKE
A PERFECT COUPLE.
- MY BELOVED GRAY, ALL I ASK
IS FOR ONE PASSIONATE GLANCE.
AWW, MY HEART
IS BEATING SO FAST!
AH, I'M SHAKING
FROM HEAD TO TOE
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT.
OH, THE ANTICIPATION!
- BUT I THINK THE TWO OF YOU
WOULD MAKE A PERFECT COUPLE.
- NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
I WISH MIRA WOULD KEEP
HER CRAZY SUGGESTIONS
TO HERSELF FOR ONCE.
- I'M TELLING YOU.
BE CAREFUL.
- Lucy: AT LEAST I'M HOME.
WHAT THE--
- YO.
- WOULD YOU STOP
BREAKING INTO MY HOUSE?
- I'M SORRY, BUT THERE'S
SOMETHING REALLY IMPORTANT
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
- OH, MAN.
LET ME GUESS, YOU DON'T
WANT TO GO BACK TO WORK.
( gasps )
- Narrator: "LIKE?!"
- WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
NATSU MIGHT HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOU.
- ( gasping )
( shrieks )
- HMM?
- OH, WOULD YOU
PLEASE GET OUT?!
- BUT I GOT TO
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
- SOMETHING IMPORTANT?
GET OUT OF HERE!
- HUH? WHOA.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
THERE'S NO NEED TO BE RUDE.
- WOULD YOU GO OUT
THROUGH THE DOOR, YOU DOPE?
- OH NO.
WHY DO I FEEL SO FUNNY?
- Narrator: THE NEXT DAY...
- ( chewing )
( sighs )
WHAT'LL I DO TODAY?
- HEY, YA!
- ( muffled scream )
- SO HOW'S IT GOING?
- HANDS OFF! PLEASE DON'T
JUST DRAPE YOURSELF
OVER ME LIKE THAT.
- HOLD ON, WHAT?
- WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
I CAN'T GET THESE
STUPID THOUGHTS OUT OF MY HEAD.
- NATSU, I'M SICK OF THIS!
STOP ACTING LIKE AN IDIOT!
- WHAT DOES IT
MATTER TO YOU, HUH?
YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME?
- LET'S RUMBLE!
- ( grunting )
- MY BELOVED GRAY,
YESTERDAY, I WAS SO NERVOUS,
I COULD BARELY EVEN MOVE,
BUT, TODAY, I'VE GOT THE COURAGE
TO GO THROUGH WITH MY PLAN.
SO HOW EXACTLY DOES
THIS POTION WORK?
- ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS BLOW THE BUBBLES
RIGHT TOWARDS
THE MAN YOU DESIRE
AND MAKE SURE
HE INHALES THEM.
IF YOU'RE SUCCESSFUL,
YOUR INTENDED WILL BECOME AWARE
OF THE FEELINGS YOU HAVE
DEEP WITHIN YOUR HEART,
PROVIDED THEY ARE STRONG ENOUGH.
- ( growling )
- ( cheering )
- DEAR SWEET GRAY,
THE LESS YOU NOTICE
MY BLAZING HEART,
THE BRIGHTER MY FLAMES
OF LOVE BECOME.
AND WHEN I'M NEAR YOU,
I'M CONSUMED BY
LUSTFUL TEMPTATION.
BUT THINGS ARE ABOUT TO CHANGE.
ONE TASTE OF THIS POTION
AND YOU'LL FINALLY BE MINE!
OUR TWO HEARTS
WILL BECOME AS ONE.
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
WE'LL BE SWEETHEARTS...
FOREVER.
- WHA-- I TOTALLY FORGOT.
I GOT TO GO TAKE CARE
OF SOMETHING.
- WHAT KIND OF
EXCUSE IS THAT?
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE THIS,
BUT I THINK NATSU'S GOT
A CRUSH ON SOME GIRL.
- WAIT, YOU MEAN OUR NATSU?
- THERE'S NO WAY, MAN.
- YOU GOT TO BE JOKING.
HE'S THE LAST GUY
I'D EVER IMAGINE
GETTING TANGLED UP
WITH SOME CHICK.
- I KNOW WHAT I HEARD, GUYS.
LATELY, HE'S BEEN
SAYING STUFF LIKE,
"I WANT TO SEE HER.
I GOT TO SEE HER."
- "HER" WHO?
- BEATS ME.
- OH CRAP!
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?!
I'M THE "HER!"
IT'S NOT LIKE I HATE HIM
OR ANYTHING.
I'M JUST NOT SURE
IF WE'D BE COMPATIBLE.
OF COURSE I'VE NEVER GONE OUT
WITH A BOY BEFORE,
SO HOW CAN I REALLY
BE SURE OF ANYTHING?
- I WANT TO SEE YOU.
- LET'S STOP IMAGINING HIM
LOOKING ALL HUNKY
LIKE THAT, OKAY?
- ( chuckles )
- ( giggles )
WHY ARE ALL THESE CRAZY THOUGHTS
RUNNING THROUGH MY BRAIN?!
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH.  UH...
( weakly )
YEAH, I'M FINE.
- CAN YOU MEET ME TONIGHT?
THERE'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU.
- ( screams )
- WHAT DO YOU SAY WE MEET
MY BY THE SOLA TREE
IN THE MIDDLE OF
SOUTH GATE PARK?
- I CAN DO THAT, BUT CAN
YOU TELL ME WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
- ALL I CAN SAY
IS IT'S IMPORTANT.
MAKE SURE
YOU COME ALONE TONIGHT.
- IS HE BLUSHING?
HE IS.
HE'S ACTUALLY BLUSHING.
- LATER.
- UH...
UH, HEY, MIRA,
I'M JUST GONNA GO HOME
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
- COME BACK! HEY!
I WASN'T THROUGH WITH YOU.
- I'M HERE, MY LOVE.
GIVE ME YOUR PASSIONATE GAZE.
( blows )
- YOU CAN'T JUST RUN AWAY
IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT.
- ( sniffing )
( sneezes )
- OKAY, LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN.
( blows )
- ( laughter )
- ( blows )
OH, MY DARLING,
WHY MUST YOU KEEP MOVING?
AT THIS RATE,
EVERYONE IN THE GUILD
WILL BE INFATUATED
WITH ME EXCEPT YOU.
WOW, THAT'S
A DISTURBING THOUGHT.
GRAY, MY LOVE!
( blows )
- ( yawns )
- I DID IT.
- ( swallows )
- ( gasps )
- WHOA, WHAT IS THIS
STRANGE SENSATION I'M FEELING?
- I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT.
FINALLY MY BELOVED GRAY
WILL PASSIONATELY
GAZE INTO MY EYES
AND SPEAK THOSE SWEET WORDS
THAT I LONG TO HEAR.
( gasps )
- ( chewing )
HMM?
- YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE.
YOU'RE ALWAYS FLYING AROUND
FREE AS A BIRD,
TRYING TO SHOW ME UP!
- SAY WHAT?
- I'M INCREDIBLY STRONG,
BUT I CAN'T FLY!
AND YOU'RE PATHETICALLY WEAK,
BUT YOU CAN!
- AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
WE'RE EVEN!
LISTEN UP!
- ( whimpering )
- AS OF TODAY,
YOU ARE MY RIVAL!
- ( screams )
- WHAT IN THE HECK
HAS GOTTEN INTO HIM?
- COME ON, LET ME
SEE WHAT YOU GOT, CAT!
- SOMEBODY HELP! GRAY'S
GONE ALL CRAZY IN THE HEAD!
AND HE WANTS TO FIGHT ME!
PLEASE DON'T
LET HIM HURT ME!
- BUT I DON'T GET IT.
HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE NOTICING ME.
- ( grunts )
YOU WANT TO TELL ME HOW MUCH
MONEY YOU MADE LAST MONTH?
- HA, I BET YOU IT'S MORE
THAN YOU MAKE IN A YEAR.
- YOU ONLY WISH YOU COULD
MAKE AS MUCH AS I DO.
- GIVE ME A BREAK, MAN.
EVERYONE KNOWS
I'M WORTH MORE THAN YOU.
- REMIND ME WHY
I WASTE MY TIME
HANGING OUT WITH YOU.
- IT'S CAUSE YOU WANT
TO KEEP TABS ON
YOUR COMPETITION, EH?
- ( both chuckle )
- I DRINK YOU, ALCOHOL,
YOU DON'T DRINK ME!
NOW LISTEN, YOU.
I'M MORE THAN STRONG ENOUGH
TO KICK YOUR
WELL-FERMENTED HIDE.
WE WERE DESTINED
BY FATE TO BE RIVALS!
- YOU SERIOUSLY THINK
ALCOHOL'S YOUR RIVAL, MASTER?
THAT'S WEIRD.
- ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
ALL OF IT IN GENERAL
OR JUST THAT BARREL
IN FRONT OF YOU?
- YOU THINK YOU CAN DRINK ME?!
I'LL NEVER LET THAT HAPPEN!
( gulping )
- CURSE YOU, WRETCHED PILLAR!
WHY MUST YOU BLOCK MY PATH,
SHATTERING MY DREAMS OF PASSING
THROUGH HERE UNHINDERED?
ANSWER ME, SCOUNDREL!
IS SILENCE YOUR WAY OF
CHALLENGING ME TO FIGHT YOU?
FROM THE MOMENT I MET YOU,
I KNEW WE WOULD BE RIVALS.
- I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU CAN BE RIVALS WITH
AN INANIMATE OBJECT, ERZA.
- THE ALCOHOL THING
KIND OF MAKES SENSE,
BUT AGAINST A PILLAR?
THAT'S JUST CRAZY.
- PUT IT WOULD MAKE
SENSE IF SHE WAS
TALKING ABOUT
A CATERPILLAR, RIGHT?
- I'LL PRETEND
YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT.
- BRING IT ON, RED!
LET'S FIGHT LIKE WE USED TO
BACK IN THE OLD DAYS.
BUT THIS TIME,
I'M NOT HOLDING BACK
'CAUSE THERE'S
NO WAY I'M GONNA LOSE
TO MY LIFELONG RIVAL.
- I'M SO CONFUSED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON!
NATSU, WHERE ARE YOU?!
- Gray: I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU!
BRING IT ON, CAT!
JUST YOU WATCH.
I'M GONNA FLY FARTHER
AND FASTER
THAN YOU EVER COULD.
- DON'T DO THIS.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
- SHUT YOUR TRAP.
I CAN FLY.
ANYTHING THAT YOU CAN DO,
I CAN DO
100 TIMES BETTER.
YOU HEAR ME, CAT?
I'LL BEAT YOU!
- THIS STINKS.
WHY IS EVERYONE GOING CRAZY?
- THE OLD MAN
DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THERE BEING A TIME DELAY
BEFORE THE POTION KICKS IN.
- Narrator: BEFORE OUR VIEWERS
GET TOO CONFUSED,
I THINK AN EXPLANATION
IS IN ORDER.
- ( chuckles )
THE FLASK I SOLD
THAT NAIVE GIRL
WAS FILLED WITH A MIXTURE
OF BANNED POTIONS
I HAPPENED TO HAVE ON HAND.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT'LL DO TO THAT POOR GUY.
YOU MAY BE ASKING YOURSELF
"HOW COULD I DO
SOMETHING SO CRUEL?"
I'M SKIPPING TOWN TONIGHT,
SO WHY SHOULD I CARE?
- Narrator:
WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
I WONDER WHAT WILL HAPPEN
TO OUR FAIRY TAIL FRIENDS.
- THIS IS GETTING WEIRD.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- Natsu: WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE MEET BY THE SOLA TREE
IN THE MIDDLE OF
SOUTH GATE PARK?
ALL I CAN SAY
IS IT'S IMPORTANT.
MAKE SURE
YOU COME ALONE TONIGHT.
- WHAT THE HECK
AM I GONNA DO?
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT HE'S GONNA
CONFESS HIS LOVE FOR ME.
I'LL HAVE TO TURN HIM DOWN,
EVEN THOUGH
IT'LL MAKE THINGS AWKWARD
SINCE WE'RE
ON THE SAME TEAM AND ALL.
I'M SO SORRY, NATSU.
THIS IS THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO WEAR MY NEW DRESS.
YES, I LOOK
SMOKING HOT IN THIS.
WAIT, THAT'S A BAD THING.
OH, DON'T BE STUPID.
WHY AM I DOING THIS?
WHAT AM I THINKING?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
OH, I GOT IT.
OPEN, GATE OF THE GIANT CRAB.
CANCER!
- ( doorbell rings )
- Cancer: CANCER.
- I WANT A SALON-PERFECT LOOK.
- YOU GOT IT, BABY.
- I SHOULDN'T BE GETTING
ALL DOLLED UP FOR HIM!
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
I STILL FIXED IT UP MYSELF.
- HEY THERE, LADY.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
LET'S HAVE 33 BABIES TOGETHER.
OKAY, LUCY?
- HMM.
- ( cries )
- I'M ALL FIRED UP.
- ( laughs )
HOW COULD I EVEN
DREAM THAT UP?!
AND WHY DID OUR KIDS
LOOK LIKE HAPPY?!
- Cana: MASTER!
I'VE COME TO CHALLENGE YOU!
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SEE
WHO'D WIN AT DRINKING!
- YOU AREN'T WORTHY
TO CALL YOURSELF MY RIVAL!
MY ENEMY IS ALCOHOL ITSELF!
- YOU'LL NEVER WIN!
( gulping )
- THREE AGAINST THREE IS IT?
YOU MAY POSSESS
THE SAME NUMBERS AS WE DO,
BUT OUR SKILLS ARE
CLEARLY SUPERIOR TO YOURS.
- WHAT KIND OF TRASH
ARE YOU TALKING?
EVERYONE KNOWS WE'RE
THE STRONGEST THREE-MAN TEAM.
YOU GUYS WANT TO FIGHT US?
- WHY DOESN'T THIS GUILD
HAVE ANY REAL MEN
IN IT'S RANKS?
I CAN'T FIND A WORTHY RIVAL?
THIS SITUATION MAKES ME SAD.
SUCH VIOLENT SADNESS...
- Max: SO, IS HE LOOKING FOR
A FIGHT OR FOR A MAN?
- Warren: I DON'T THINK I WANT
TO STICK AROUND TO FIND OUT.
- OKAY, YOU FINISHED
TALLYING UP YOUR NUMBERS?
- YEAH, I WAS DONE
A LONG TIME AGO, YOU SLOWPOKE.
JUST WAITING ON YOU.
LOOKS LIKE I'M BETTER
THAN YOU IN EVERY WAY.
- YEAH, RIGHT, BUDDY.
WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO SEE ABOUT THAT.
- OKAY, WHEN I SAY GO...
- BRING IT ON!
LAST MONTH, I EARNED EXACTLY...
- Both: READY GO!
150,000!
( gasps )
WE MADE THE SAME AMOUNT?
WE'LL HAVE TO GO
BY THE MONTH BEFORE!
- OUR THUNDER LEGION
AGAINST YOUR SHADOW GEAR.
LET'S FIND OUT
ONCE AND FOR ALL
WHO THE BEST
THREE-MAN TEAM IS
IN ALL OF FAIRY TAIL!
- I HOPE YOU WON'T BE
TOO DISAPPOINTED
AFTER WE WIPE
THE FLOOR WITH YOU!
- HOW DARE YOU!
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHO YOU'RE MESSING WITH.
- Both: ARE THEY
HAVING A POSE-OFF?
- LET'S SEE WHAT
YOU GOT, GRAMPS!
- I'VE ONLY JUST BEGUN!
- WHERE ARE ALL THE REAL MEN?!
- WATCH OUT, LUCY.
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
- I'LL BE OKAY.
- HEY!
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD
IN THAT DRESS YOU GOT ON.
NOW DON'T YOU GO
FALLING INTO THE RIVER
BEFORE YOUR BIG DATE.
- WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY "DATE"?
THERE'S NO DENYING.
I AM LOOKING GOOD.
( gasps )
BUT IT'S NOT A DATE!
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW CUTE I MAY LOOK.
( gasps )
( sighs )
( grunts )
NO, THIS IS BAD.
I CAN'T START CRUSHING
ON SOMEONE I WORK WITH.
BUT MAYBE BEING ON
THE SAME TEAM IS A GOOD THING.
WE'LL ALWAYS BE TOGETHER.
- WE'LL BE
TOGETHER FOREVER, LUCY.
- FOREVER AND EVER.
WHA!
- REQUIP: HEAVEN'S WHEEL!
( shouts )
( grunts )
- COME ON, ERZA,
CUT IT OUT!
- IT TOOK US A LONG TIME
TO REBUILD THE PLACE.
DON'T GO AND WRECK IT.
- SILENCE!
THIS VILE PILLAR INSISTS
ON STANDING IN MY WAY.
I NEED TO GO FURTHER INSIDE
AND YET IT BLOCKS MY PATH!
AND THEN IT SECRETLY MOCKS ME
WHEN I HAVE TO TAKE TIME
TO WALK AROUND IT!
IT'S UNRELENTING IN
IT'S OBSTRUCTION OF MY COURSE.
WHY WOULD IT DO THAT UNLESS
IT WAS MY GREATEST RIVAL?
- HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
TAKING A DIFFERENT ROUTE
THROUGH THE HALL?
- I KNOW YOU'RE
SET IN YOUR WAYS,
BUT THIS IS A BIT MUCH.
- I THINK ERZA'S
FINALLY FOUND AN OPPONENT
THAT'S JUST AS STUBBORN
AS SHE IS.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- GET YOUR BUTT OVER HERE
AND FIGHT ME, ERZA.
IT'S TIME WE FINISH THIS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- ARE YOU BLIND? CAN'T YOU SEE
I'M IN THE MIDST OF BATTLE
WITH MY LIFELONG RIVAL?
- NOT REALLY.
IT'S JUST A PILLAR.
IT CAN'T FIGHT BACK.
- ( growling )
I WON'T BE IGNORED!
SATAN SOUL!
- Both: MIRA, NO!
- THAT'S IT!
REQUIP: PURGATORY ARMOR!
- CAN'T WE TALK
ABOUT THIS, LADIES?
- FACE MY FIERCE LYNX PUNCH!
- ( screams )
- WHERE'S MY RIVAL?
I'VE GOT TO FIND A REAL MAN!
- MOVE IT!
- MAN, IT'S NO USE.
- GUESS THE GUILD HALL'S
GONNA GET DESTROYED AGAIN.
- ( fighting )
- THEN...
- PLEASE, GRAY,
YOU GOT TO LISTEN TO ME.
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
- SHUT YOUR FACE.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA LET YOU TALK
YOUR WAY OUT OF THIS ONE.
- Juvia: NO, THIS ISN'T WORKING.
MAYBE HE NEEDS MORE POTION.
( blows )
- ALL RIGHT, IT'S TIME
TO DO THIS, HAPPY.
FOLLOW ME IF YOU CAN.
( screams )
- WOW, WHAT'S
HAPPENING TO HIM?
- ( grunts )
NOW I'M EVEN MORE FIRED UP!
- WHY IS HE ACTING LIKE NATSU
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WATCH ME FLY.
( growls )
- ( screams )
- ( grunting )
I'M GONNA FLY!
JUST WATCH ME!
BEHOLD, I AM THE WIND.
- Narrator: THE SOLA TREE
IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOUTH GATE PARK.
- STAY CALM.
YOU'VE GOT THIS.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO GET ALL NERVOUS.
JUST KEEP IT TOGETHER.
- HEY, YOU MADE IT.
AH! YEAH.
HE'S HERE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- ( laughs )
- OH MAN, I'M SUCH A PUSHOVER
WHEN IT COMES TO
THIS KIND OF STUFF.
- ( grunts ) IT SURE
TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
NOW HURRY UP AND SUMMON
THAT MAID OF YOURS.
YOU KNOW, WHAT'S HER NAME?
COME ON.
OH YEAH, VIRGO.
YOU SEE, THE GROUND HERE IS
TOO TOUGH FOR ME TO DIG THROUGH.
ONLY THAT CELESTIAL MAID
YOU'VE GOT COULD GET PAST IT.
- HOLD ON, YOU SAID YOU HAD
SOMETHING IMPORTANT TO SAY?
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE THIS,
BUT THERE'S AN AMAZING
TREASURE BURIED HERE.
SOMEBODY TOLD ME THAT
THERE'S A PHOTO ALBUM
CHOCK-FULL OF
EMBARRASSING PICTURES
OF ALMOST EVERY MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL.
AND THEY TOLD ME THAT GRAMPS
BURIED IT HERE TO HIDE IT.
SO I REALLY
WANT TO DIG IT UP.
- UM, I HEARD YOU--
THAT IS,
I OVERHEARD SOMEONE SAY
THAT YOU HAD
A CRUSH ON A GIRL.
- HUH?
- EVERYONE WAS TALKING ABOUT
HOW YOU KEPT SAYING
"I WANT TO SEE HER."
- I WAS JUST
LOOKING FOR VIRGO.
IT'S NOT LIKE I GOT FEELINGS
FOR HER OR NOTHING.
I WAS REALLY JUST HOPING
I COULD GET HER
TO DIG THIS HOLE FOR ME.
- YOU WERE, HUH?
THAT'S IMPORTANT?!
DIGGING A HOLE?!
( growls )
- ( slaps )
- OWW! OH.
OH, WHOA, WHAT THE--
- WHAT WAS I THINKING?
HOW CAN I BE
SUCH AN IDIOT?
- Narrator: AND SO LUCY'S
BAD LUCK WITH MEN
HAS CROSSED INTO A SECOND
CONSECUTIVE EPISODE.
- ( rooster crows )
- DOES ANYONE KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
- UH...
- Both: IT'S FINALLY OVER.
- COME ON.
GEEZ, IT'S MORNING ALREADY.
YOU REALLY GOT TO
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
JUVIA, MAYBE YOU CAN
KNOCK SOME SENSE INTO HIM.
- MY DARLING GRAY,
OH, PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I'M THE REASON YOU HAD
TO SUFFER THROUGH ALL OF THIS.
IT'S CLEAR NOW WHY THE POTION
DIDN'T WORK PROPERLY.
IT CAN ONLY BE THAT
MY FEELINGS FOR YOU
WEREN'T QUITE STRONG ENOUGH.
MY BELOVED.
- HEY, JUVIA.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
- THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE WELL AGAIN.
- SHE LOVES YOU.
- I WAS WONDERING WHY
I FELT SO COLD ALL OF A SUDDEN.
I ALWAYS END UP SOAKING WET
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND.
YOU KNOW I HATE THAT.
- HEARTBREAKING,
HOW CAN HE BE SO COLD?
- HUH? IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- I'VE BEEN SO PATIENT,
BUT I CAN'T TAKE IT ANY MORE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
YOU'LL HAVE TO
DRINK DOWN EVERY DROP!
- ( gulping )
( screams )
- I'M RIGHT OVER HERE, MY LOVE.
- LISTEN UP,
ARROGANT HORIZON!
YOU ARE MY RIVAL NOW!
- GRAY, MY BELOVED,
PLEASE LOVE ME.
- I GUESS THERE
ARE SOME PEOPLE
WHO ARE SIMPLY NEVER
MEANT TO FLY.
- Narrator: AND SO IT SEEMS THAT
JUVIA'S BAD LUCK WITH MEN
RIVALS THAT OF LUCY.
JUST A FEW DAYS LATER...
- ( sighs )
SO BORED.
- HEY, LUCY.
- WHAT'S UP?
- NOTHING REALLY.
JUST A PASSING THOUGHT.
DO YOU THINK GRAY
MIGHT HAVE A THING FOR YOU?
YOU'D BE SO CUTE TOGETHER.
- OH, DON'T YOU
EVEN GO THERE.
I CAN'T GO THROUGH
THAT AGAIN!
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT?
A SPELL TO MAKE PEOPLE
FALL IN LOVE?
I DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING LIKE THAT?
- WAIT A SECOND.
COULD SOMEONE PLEASE EXPLAIN
HOW I ENDED UP HERE?
- IT COULD ONLY BE THE CURSE
OF THE MOON, YOUNG MAN.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: WHAT'S THAT?
SOME GUYS FROM A DARK GUILD
ARE CAUSING PROBLEMS?
BIG SURPRISE.  DON'T WORRY.
I'LL JUST GO OVER THERE
AND KICK THEIR BUTTS.
- Happy: YOU CAN'T.
THEY'VE GOT HOSTAGES.
AND KNOWING YOU,
YOU'D BEAT THEM UP
ALONG WITH THE BAD GUYS.
- OH, YOU KNOW WHAT, JUST
FOR THAT LITTLE COMMENT,
I'M GOING.
- I SAID YOU CAN'T.
AND I MEAN IT.
- WELL, HOW DO YOU SUGGEST
I GET MORE SCENES?
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
YOU WERE GONNA GO?
- DIDN'T YOU NOTICE
THE SERIOUS LACK OF NATSU
IN THIS EPISODE?
- SORRY, PAL.
BUT NOT EVERYBODY
CAN BE A STAR LIKE ME.