- Natsu: LISANNA!
WHERE DID YOU GO?
WOULD YOU QUIT PLAYING
AROUND ALREADY,
COME ON AND SAY SOMETHING.
OW. THIS STINKS.
- ( Lisanna screaming )
- LISANNA.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- JUST A DREAM.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA STEAL MY BED,
YOU COULD AT LEAST TRY
TO LOOK A LITTLE HAPPIER.
THAT'S IT, I'M DONE DOING
NICE THINGS FOR YOU.
I HAD TO SLEEP ON THE
COLD HARD FLOOR
AND THIS IS THE KIND OF
THANKS YOU GIVE ME?
- GEEZ, LUCY. DO YOU
HAVE TO BE SO LOUD
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING?
- IF YOU TWO ARE GONNA
KEEP FREELOADING OF ME,
I CAN BE AS LOUD AS I WANT,
WHENEVER I FEEL LIKE IT. OKAY?
- IT'S TOTALLY WORTH IT, THOUGH.
THIS BED IS LIKE A FLUFFY CLOUD
FLOATING OVER DREAMLAND.
- AYE!
- THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD
BUY ONE FOR YOURSELF.
- YOU WANNA GRAB SOME BREAKFAST?
- AYE.
- SO WHAT WERE YOU
DREAMING ABOUT?
- WHAT?
- YOU JUST WOKE UP FROM
A NIGHTMARE, DIDN'T YOU?
- Natsu: ( chuckles )
NOW I'M DREAMING ABOUT FOOD.
- Happy: AYE, SIR! - Lucy:
YOU'RE NOT GETTING ANY OF MINE.
- Happy: GILDARTS.
- GOTTA SAY, YOU TWO ARE LOOKING
RIGHT AT HOME AT FAIRY TAIL.
- YEAH.
- ACTUALLY, WE LIVE IN THE
GIRLS-ONLY DORM.
- HOW COME YOU DON'T LIVE
THERE TOO, LUCY?
IT'S REALLY NICE AND COZY.
- YEAH, WELL, I DIDN'T
FIND OUT ABOUT IT
UNTIL AFTER I GOT MY PLACE.
BESIDES, THE RENT
THERE IS LIKE
A HUNDRED THOUSAND
JEWEL A MONTH.
MY APARTMENT IS WAY MORE
AFFORDABLE AND I'M BROKE.
- ( chuckling )
- Both: BIG NEWS!
- ( church bells ringing )
- ( people gasping )
- WHAT'S UP?
- SOUNDS LIKE BELLS.
- I BET I KNOW WHY THEY'RE
RINGING. - AYE!
- YEAH.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
- THERE THEY GO.
- OH, MAN!
- KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS!
- OLD GILDARTS IS
COMING BACK HOME.
- OH YEAH!
- All: GILDARTS IS BACK!
- GILDARTS? WHO'S THAT?
ARE THEY IN A GUILD?
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER EVEN
HEARD OF THEM BEFORE.
- HE'S THE STRONGEST WIZARD
IN FAIRYTAIL.
- OH. ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I THOUGHT ERZA WAS
TOP DOG AROUND HERE.
- ALL MODESTY ASIDE, I DON'T
EVEN HOLD A CANDLE TO HIM.
- I'LL BET THAT THIS GUY MUST BE
THE KING OF BREAKING STUFF THEN.
- ( people cheering )
- WELL, IT'S GOOD HE'S BACK,
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
EVERYONE'S GOING TOTALLY NUTS.
- LOOK HOW HAPPY THEY ALL ARE!
- THEY'RE CERTAINLY MORE
OUT OF CONTROL THAN USUAL.
- IT'S ONLY NATURAL
EVERYONE'S EXCITED.
HE'S BEEN GONE QUITE A WHILE.
THREE YEARS IN FACT.
- THAT'S SO CRAZY.
SO WHAT HAS HE BEEN DOING?
- Mirajane: WELL, WE HAVE
REGULAR JOBS AND S-CLASS QUESTS.
ABOVE THOSE ARE SS-CLASS QUESTS.
AND ABOVE THOSE ARE JOBS
CALLED DECADE QUESTS.
- DECADE QUESTS?
- Erza: THEY'RE JOBS THAT
NO ONE HAS BEEN ABLE
TO COMPLETE IN LESS
THAN TEN YEARS.
THUS, THE NAME, DECADE QUEST.
ACTUALLY, GILDARTS TOOK ON AN
EVEN HIGHER LEVEL JOB THAN THAT.
A CENTURY QUEST.
- Lucy: YOU'VE GOT TO
BE KIDDING!
WHO IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
WOULD TAKE ON A JOB
THAT LASTS A HUNDRED YEARS?
- HIM.
- GILDARTS IS BACK!
- EVERYBODY BETTER
GET READY FOR HIM!
- PREPARE TO COMMENCE MAGNOLIA'S
GILDARTS SHIFT.
CITIZENS, PLEASE TAKE YOUR
DESIGNATED POSITIONS
IMMEDIATELY.
- I'M ALL FOR FESTIVE,
BUT THIS IS JUST RIDICULOUS.
- THEY SURE ARE EXCITED.
- WHAT THE HECK IS A "MAGNOLIA
GILDARTS SHIFT," ANYWAY?
- STEP OUTSIDE AND
SEE FOR YOURSELF.
- ( bells ringing )
- ( rumbling )
- ( exclaiming )
- ARE WE HAVING AN EARTHQUAKE?
- MAGNOLIA JUST SPLIT IN TWO.
- A PRECAUTIONARY MEASURE FOR
GILDARTS' CRASH MAGIC.
- SINCE HE DESTROYS EVERYTHING
THAT HE TOUCHES,
IT'S MUCH BETTER FOR
EVERYONE IF HE STAYS CLEAR
OF THEIR HOMES AND BUSINESSES.
- LIKE HE JUST WALKS RIGHT
THROUGH THEM?
YOU MODIFIED THE TOWN JUST
'CAUSE HE'S CLUMSY?
- Wendy: HE SOUNDS AMAZING!
- Carla: YES. AMAZINGLY STUPID.
- Natsu: HERE HE COMES!
- Happy: AYE!
- COME ON, YA OLD GEEZER,
LET'S THROW DOWN.
- THAT'S NO WAY TO TREAT A MAN.
- WELCOME HOME.
- HE'S THE MOST POWERFUL
GUY IN THE GUILD?
- SORRY TO BOTHER YOU, MISS.
BUT I'M LOOKING FOR A
GUILD THAT USED TO BE
AROUND THESE PARTS
CALLED FAIRY TAIL.
- THIS IS IT. REMEMBER ME?
MIRAJANE.
- HUH? MIRA?
WOW.
YOU SURE HAVE GROWN UP A LOT,
LITTLE GIRL.
AND DID YOU CHANGE SOME STUFF
AROUND THE HALL, TOO?
- HE DIDN'T NOTICE THAT
FROM OUTSIDE?
- GILDARTS!
- NATSU. HEY PAL.
THERE'S SOMEONE I RECOGNIZE.
- ( chuckling )
GOOD TO SEE YA.
NOW LET'S PARTY.
( exclaiming )
- NOT NOW, KID.
- ( chuckles ) OH YEAH.
HE'S STILL SO AWESOME.
- SAME OL' TOUGH GUY
WE'VE ALWAYS KNOWN.
- GENUINE, OLD FASHIONED
MAN'S MAN.
- I SEE A COUPLE OF NEW FACES
AROUND HERE, TOO.
A LOT HAPPENED WHILE I WAS GONE.
- GILDARTS.
- OH, MASTER.
YOU'RE LOOKING WELL.
- HOW'D THE JOB GO?
- HMM.
( laughing )
- ( sighs )
- NO GOOD.
WAY TOO MUCH FOR ME.
- ( crowd gasping )
- NO WAY. BUT THAT'S GILDARTS.
- HE FAILED?
- HE'S JOKING, RIGHT?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'D JUST
GIVE UP LIKE THIS.
- I GUESS IT TAKES A BIG MAN
TO ADMIT DEFEAT.
- THE CENTURY QUEST IS TOO MUCH
FOR EVEN THE STRONGEST
WIZARD IN FAIRY TAIL?
I WONDER WHAT IT TAKES TO
FINISH IT.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING
OVER THERE AND YOU SHOULD STOP.
THERE'S NO WAY.
- Oh. I WASN'T THINKING ABOUT
ANYTHING AT ALL, I SWEAR.
MY MIND IS TOTALLY BLANK.
- I SEE.
THE JOB WAS TOO TOUGH.
- FORGIVE ME FOR BRINGING
SHAME TO THE GUILD.
- NO.
YOU'VE ONLY BROUGHT YOURSELF
BACK IN ONE PIECE.
THAT'S NO SMALL FEAT IN ITSELF.
AS FAR AS I KNOW,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S MADE THE
JOURNEY HOME ALIVE.
- ( chuckles )
THANKS, BOSS.
NOW I GOTTA GET BACK HOME
AND START TO ACTUALLY
FEEL ALIVE.
REST MY WEARY BONES.
OH, NATSU.
STOP BY LATER.
I BROUGHT SOMETHING BACK FOR YA.
WELL, I'M OUTTA HERE, YOU GUYS.
- ( crowd gasping )
- I WAS AFRAID OF THAT.
- YOU CAN USE THE FRONT DOOR,
YA KNOW?
- ( laughs ) WONDER WHAT
THE OLD MAN'S GOT FOR ME.
I'M FIRED UP JUST
THINKING ABOUT IT.
- ONE WALL BREAKER
AROUND HERE IS ENOUGH.
- OH MY GOODNESS.
- COME ON, HAPPY.
WE'RE OUTTA HERE TOO.
- Huh. ARE THIS GILDARTS GUY
AND NATSU, LIKE,
ESPECIALLY CLOSE OR SOMETHING?
- AYE. GILDARTS IS
ON A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT LEVEL THAN NATSU,
BUT THEY'VE STILL BEEN
PRETTY GOOD FRIENDS
FOR AS LONG AS THEY'VE
KNOWN EACH OTHER.
- Lucy: OH YEAH? BUT ISN'T HE
GONE OUT ON QUESTS
MOST OF THE TIME?
- AYE.
BUT HE WAS AROUND ABOUT
THE TIME I WAS BORN,
SO I'VE KNOWN HIM MY WHOLE LIFE.
- Happy: WHEN DO I GET
MY FISHY-WISHY?
- Natsu: HOLD YOUR HORSES. I'M
JUST ABOUT TO LAND A HUGE ONE.
- Lisanna: THEY DON'T SEEM TO
BE BITING, DO THEY?
- Happy: SHE DIDN'T FISH, BUT
LISANNA WAS WITH US THAT DAY.
- WHAT DID I TELL YA?
- BRING THAT SUCKER IN.
- YES!
- IT'S TINY!
- IT'S SMALL,
BUT IT'LL FEED US, RIGHT?
- I GUESS, BUT THAT HUGE ONE
YOU WERE GONNA LAND
WOULD'VE FED US EVEN BETTER.
- I'LL GET A BIGGER ONE,
JUST NOT TODAY, OKAY?
- ( giggling )
- IT'S JUST LIKE WATCHING
A LITTLE KID ASKING HIS DAD
TO GIVE HIM A BETTER TOY.
- NO IT'S NOT,
'CUZ I'M NOT HIS DAD.
- I'D DEFINITELY NEVER
SEE HIM AS A FATHER FIGURE.
- WELL, I WOULDN'T
MIND BEING THE MOM,
BECAUSE THAT WOULD
MEAN I'M LIKE YOUR WIFE.
- DON'T START THAT AGAIN.
YOU AND ME AREN'T MARRIED, OKAY?
- THEN WHY ARE YOU
BLUSHING LIKE THAT?
IT'LL BE TRUE SOME DAY,
WON'T IT?
- NO IT WON'T, YA BIG DUMMY.
- YOU ARE JUST THE CUTEST
WHEN YOU'RE EMBARRASSED.
- OH, NATSU, SHE LOVES YOU.
- THAT IS GONNA
GET OLD REAL QUICK.
- ( snoring )
- SO TELL ME,
DO YOU EVER REMEMBER
ANYTHING ABOUT YOUR
MOM OR DAD, NATSU?
JUST CURIOUS.
MY BROTHER AND SISTER ARE SUPER
NICE AND TAKE GOOD CARE OF ME,
SO IT'S NOT LIKE I DON'T HAVE
A FAMILY OR ANYTHING.
BUT I WONDER WHAT IT'D BE LIKE.
JUST TO FEEL A PARENT'S WARMTH.
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
- DO YOU EVER FEEL THAT WAY?
- MAYBE. I MEAN I GUESS THAT
I KNEW IGNEEL'S WARMTH.
- YOUR DRAGON?
OH.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY? WHY DID HE LEAVE ME?
I TRIED REALLY HARD TO FIND HIM.
I LOOKED EVERYWHERE.
BUT IT WAS JUST NO USE AT ALL.
HE LEFT.
- IT'S SO SAD.
I ALMOST FORGOT TO TELL YOU,
I FOUND SOME GIANT FOOTPRINTS
ON THE EDGE OF THE EAST FOREST.
- WHAT? FOR REAL?
- YEAH. I'M NOT SURE IF
THEY WERE DRAGON TRACKS
BUT THEY SEEMED
BIG ENOUGH TO ME.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO CHECK 'EM OUT!
- I DON'T KNOW,
THE SUN'S ABOUT TO SET.
- WHO THE HECK CARES.
I'LL GO BY MYSELF IF I GOTTA.
TELL ME WHERE YOU FOUND EM.
- WHAT'RE YOU YELLING ABOUT?
- I'LL GO TOO, OKAY?
I'LL SHOW YOU.
- OH YEAH.
I'M FIRED UP NOW.
- IT'S GETTING KINDA SCARY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
SO, DO YA SEE EM' OR WHAT?
- NOT YET, BUT I THINK WE'RE
GETTING PRETTY CLOSE TO 'EM.
RIGHT HERE.
- WOW, THOSE ARE FOOTPRINTS?
THEY'RE SO BIG.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK, NATSU?
- I THINK THESE ARE FROM
A FOREST VULCAN.
- HUH? ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT ONE OF THOSE BIG MONSTERS
LIKE THAT GORIAN YOU
FOUGHT THAT ONE TIME?
- ( sighs )
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN BETTER.
I MEAN, I LOOKED
ALL OVER FOR IGNEEL,
THERE'S NO WAY HE'D JUST HAPPEN
TO SHOW UP SO CLOSE BY.
- I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET YOUR HOPES UP.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
START HEADING HOME.
- MMM-HMM.
- WHERE IS HE?
WHERE DID IGNEEL GO?
- NATSU!
WAIT FOR ME.
( panting )
YOU'RE WALKING A LITTLE
TOO FAST FOR ME.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- IT'S GETTING SUPER FOGGY.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- HEY, SHOULDN'T WE WAIT AND
LET LISANNA CATCH UP?
- OH, YEAH.
HEY, COME ON, HURRY UP.
IS SHE STILL BACK THERE?
- I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD'VE
WAITED FOR HER.
- UH-OH. IF WORD GETS OUT
THAT I LOST HER OUT HERE,
I'M GONNA BE IN
SERIOUS TROUBLE.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE MY FRIEND.
- GET READY FOR THE BEATING
OF YOUR LIFE, YOU LITTLE PUNK.
- MIRAJANE'S RIGHT.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
VERY PAINFUL.
- HOLD ON LISANNA,
I'M COMING FOR YA.
LISANNA.
WHERE DID YOU GO?
WOULD YOU QUIT PLAYING
AROUND ALREADY.
C'MON AND SAY SOMETHING.
OW. THIS STINKS.
- ( Lisanna screaming )
- ( laughing )
- THERE IT IS.
- LONG TIME, NO SEE,
YA LITTLE PUNK.
YOU AIN'T LOOKIN' FOR THIS,
ARE YOU?
- HELP ME.
- LISANNA! LET HER GO.
GET YOUR HANDS
OFF OF HER, MONKEY.
- NO WAY. YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW THINGS WORK
IN THE FOREST, DO YA KID?
FINDERS KEEPERS,
LOSERS WEEPERS.
- SHE ISN'T YOURS TO KEEP.
- YEAH.
- OH, I'M GONNA
KEEP HER ALRIGHT,
'CUZ IT JUST SO HAPPENS THAT
I'VE BEEN LOOKIN' FOR A WIFE.
- A WIFE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
- YOU SEE,
THAT'S KINDA HOW I FEEL.
- OH, WOW. SCANDALOUS.
TRULY FORBIDDEN LOVE.
- I'M SORRY IF YOU FEEL
THAT WAY, MR VULCAN.
BUT MY HEART BELONGS TO MY
SWEET LITTLE NATSU.
- YEAH? WELL I SAY YOU'RE MINE,
SO THAT MEANS
YOU'RE MINE, OKAY?
- YOU DON'T MAKE THE
RULES AROUND HERE.
- YOU DISRESPECTED ME, KID.
SO I'M GONNA KEEP HER.
BUT IF YOU REALLY WANT HER BACK,
YOU SHOULD APOLOGIZE.
- NOW YOU'RE BLACKMAILING ME?
- NO. HE'S JUST
MESSING WITH YOU.
- SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE,
GET ON YOUR HANDS AND KNEES,
AND I'LL GIVE HER RIGHT BACK.
- ( sighs ) FINE.
- HE'S DOIN' IT?
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THE
WAY I TREATED YOU, SIR.
PLEASE GIVE LISANNA BACK.
- NATSU.
- IN YOUR DREAMS.
- NO! DON'T.
- THAT'S PLAYING DIRTY, YOU APE.
- ( laughs ) YOU JUST FELL FOR
THE OLDEST TRICK IN THE BOOK.
- THAT REALLY HURTS.
- OH YEAH! NOW I'M FIRED UP.
- PREPARE TO GET CRUSHED
LIKE THE LITTLE PEST YOU ARE.
- YOU REALLY ARE A NASTY,
STUPID MONKEY, YA KNOW?
- IT'S GILDARTS!
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING
NAMES, YA RUNT?
- I'LL JUST GET THIS
OUTTA THE WAY.
- LET ME EXPLAIN TO YOU HOW THIS
THING IS GONNA GO FROM HERE.
YOU'RE GONNA LET GO OF THE GIRL,
TURN AROUND, AND WALK AWAY.
- I HEAR YA LOUD AND CLEAR.
I'M SORRY, SIR.
- THANKS A LOT!
- DO I KNOW YOU, LITTLE GIRL?
- YES, I'M LISANNA.
- I'LL BE, YOU'RE
MIRAJANE'S KID SISTER.
- NATSU, ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
- YEAH.
- DOES ANYBODY ELSE SEE
A FLYING CAT OVER THERE,
OR AM I GOING NUTS?
- THAT'S JUST OUR NEWEST
GUILD MEMBER, HAPPY.
- SORRY, GILDARTS, BUT...
- YOU'VE GROWN UP TO
BE QUITE THE MAN, NATSU.
- HUH?
THERE'S A WHOLE LOT
MORE TO BEING A WIZARD
THAN JUST HAVING
MAGICAL POWER.
IT'S ABOUT HAVING GUTS
AND STANDING UP FOR THOSE
WHO CAN'T HELP THEMSELVES,
NO MATTER WHAT
THE ODDS MAY BE.
AND YOU'VE GOT GUTS.
- THANKS!
- BUT. I GUESS HAVING A WIFE
IS PRETTY MANLY TOO, HUH?
- SHE'S NOT MY WIFE.
- OH, DON'T BE EMBARRASSED.
- HE LOVES HER!
- ( Glidarts laughs )
- MAN, THIS FOG
IS LIKE PEA SOUP.
- IT TENDS TO GET THICK
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
SO WATCH YOUR STEP.
- IT'S SO MAGICAL,
LIKE WE'RE WALKING AROUND
ON A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
PLANET RIGHT NOW.
- YOU THINK SO?
- EARLIER WHEN YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR ME,
IT MADE ME FEEL SO GOOD
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE
CALLING OUT MY NAME
THROUGH ALL THE MURK AND FOG.
- HMM.
- HEY.
IF I EVER WENT MISSING
LIKE THAT AGAIN,
YOU'D GO LOOKING FOR ME,
WOULDN'T YOU?
YOU WOULDN'T JUST LET
ME STAY GONE, RIGHT?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
- I KNEW YOU'D SAY YES.
- WHY NOT?
- COME BY TOMORROW, PAL.
WE'LL PLAY A LITTLE CATCH,
ALL RIGHT?
- OH YEAH!
I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
- ( Natsu grunting )
- LEMME ASK YOU. WHAT WERE
YOU DOIN' WALKIN' AROUND
THE EAST FOREST IN THE
DARK OF NIGHT, ANYWAY?
- I TOLD YA ABOUT IGNEEL BEFORE.
YOU REMEMBER, DON'T YA?
- YEAH. THAT'S THE RED DRAGON
YOU BEEN CHASING AFTER.
- LISANNA FOUND SOME FOOTPRINTS,
SO WE WENT TO LOOK FOR HIM.
BUT TURNS OUT,
SHE WAS DEAD WRONG.
- SORRY, MY BAD.
THIS IGNEEL,
I RECKON SEEING HIM AGAIN IS
PRETTY IMPORTANT
TO YA, ISN'T IT?
WITH GUTS LIKE YOU GOT,
I KNOW YOU'LL FIND HIM, KID.
- YEAH!
- NOW WHAT DO YOU SAY TO
DOIN' A LITTLE FISHIN'?
- GILDARTS IS REALLY NICE.
HE'S ALMOST LIKE
A FATHER TO HIM.
- AYE!
- WOW, MAYBE HE BROUGHT ME BACK
SOME KINDA RARE FIRE
FROM ANOTHER KINGDOM
OR SOMETHING.
- YEAH, WONDER WHAT IT IS.
- YO!
- WHAT'S UP, MAN?
- HEY, GOOD TO SEE YA.
- MAN, IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE'VE BEEN HERE.
- SEEMS LIKE IT'S BEEN FOREVER.
- SO, WHATCHA GOT FOR ME, POPS?
- NEVER MIND THAT.
HOW HAVE YOU AND LITTLE LISANNA
BEEN GETTING ALONG
SINCE I'VE BEEN GONE? HUH?
- WHAT?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO PLAY COY.
( laughs )
- LISANNA DIED,
TWO YEARS AGO.
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE SERIOUS?
I SEE. THAT'S EXPLAINS
WHY MIRA...
MY CONDOLENCES.
- IF THAT'S ALL YOU WANNA
TALK ABOUT, I'M OUT.
- NATSU, WAIT.
- LISTEN, WHILE I WAS GONE,
I MET A DRAGON.
IT'S NOT THE ONE YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR, THOUGH.
IT WAS BLACK AS
A MOONLESS NIGHT.
- WHERE WAS IT?
- SACRED MT. ZONIA.
HE'S THE REAL REASON
WHY I FAILED ON MY QUEST.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- WELL, OBVIOUSLY,
I'LL ASK HIM IF HE
KNOWS WHERE IGNEEL IS.
- THINK AGAIN, KID.
THAT BLACK ONE'S
LONG GONE BY NOW.
HE'S OUT FLYING IN
THE WILD BLUE YONDER.
- I DON'T CARE, I CAN TRACK HIM
DOWN IF I PUT MY MIND TO IT.
- NATSU, LOOK AT ME.
IT WAS OVER BEFORE
I KNEW WHAT HIT ME.
IT RIPPED OFF MY ARM.
MY LEG, AND THEN IT GUTTED ME.
IGNEEL MAY BE A DIFFERENT
KIND OF CREATURE,
BUT I'M TELLING YOU THIS BLACK
ONE IS NO FRIEND TO ANYONE.
THERE'S NOT A MAN THAT
COULD BEAT HIM.
- LOOK, WE DRAGON SLAYERS
AREN'T JUST CALLED THAT
FOR NOTHING, YA KNOW.
THIS GUY DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF.
- IF THAT'S WHAT YOU BELIEVE,
I'M NOT GONNA TRY TO
STAND IN YOUR WAY.
- ( grunting )
GOOD!
- HOLD ON!
- HEY, CAT!
BETTER MAKE SURE TO
HAVE HIS BACK, ALL RIGHT?
THERE MIGHT NOT BE A MAN OUT
THERE THAT CAN BEAT THAT THING.
BUT, MAYBE A DRAGON CAN.
THERE'S HOPE FOR NATSU.
- ( sighs )
THERE ARE NOW THREE
DRAGON SLAYERS IN THIS GUILD.
PORLYUSICA, IT IS JUST
AS YOU FORETOLD.
WE ARE STANDING ON THE
CUSP OF A NEW ERA.
- COME ON. COME ON.
I GOTTA FIND HIM.
( exclaiming )
ARE YOU OUT THERE, IGNEEL?
DAD?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: I'M SO BORED.
HEY, WHERE'D GAJEEL
RUN OFF TO?
ME AND HIM SHOULD FIGHT.
- Happy: BEING BORED IS
NO REASON TO FIGHT A GUY.
ANYWAY, IS IT JUST ME OR IS THE
SKY LOOKIN' REALLY WEIRD?
- Natsu: WHOA, YEAH. LOOKS LIKE
A STORM'S A BREWIN' FOR SURE!
- Happy: I HOPE THAT'S
ALL WE GET.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THE SKY
LOOK LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- Both: NEXT TIME, EARTH LAND.
- Natsu: IF A RAIN SHOWER IS
WHAT WE USUALLY GET,
DO YOU THINK SOMETHIN'
MORE WOULD BE LIKE A RAIN BATH?
- Happy: THAT'S NOT THE WAY
IT WORKS, NATSU.