What in the...?
I saw somethin' shiny!
[ROMEO] Didja
guys hear me?
[NATSU] Man, this
is some tasty grub!
[LUCY] Michelle made
all of this by herself!
And there's plenty
more so eat up!
[HAPPY] Aren't you
gonna have some, Romeo?!
♪
[LUCY] Let's see here...
[HAPPY] What do you think
this weird lookin' thing is?
I'm not sure but if I
had to make a guess...
It's some sort of
strange door, isn't it?
Maybe, but how do
we get it open?
[NATSU grumbles]
Gimme some
room you guys!
Wait, Natsu!
You never listen!
Uh-oh...
[NATSU screams]
I'm sorry buddy,
but your attack didn't even
leave a mark.
Did you honestly believe
that wrecking the door
was gonna help
us...? Geez!
[MICHELLE] Do you suppose
there's some sort of
trick to it?
[ROMEO] Is that
what I think it is?
Looks like
a keyhole!
Sure does...!
But we don't have
a key to open it.
I bet I know someone
who's totally cut out for this.
Hey... baby.
Do you think you can unlock
this door for us, Cancer?
These scissors are the
lifeblood of a stylist;
they're made for cuttin'
hair not pickin' locks...!
'Kay, baby?
Oh, I feel terrible!
I'm sorry!
This is all my fault...!
Please forgive me!
[CANCER] I'm a sucker for
tears... I'll do it, baby!
[LUCY] That
was easy...
Girls make us weak!
Wow, way to go!
[MICHELLE] Isn't
he wonderful?
Piece of cake... baby!
[LUCY] Um... I've got a
bad feeling about this...
[rumbling]
[screams]
[HAPPY] Labyrinth Capriccio!
[JUVIA] Gray, my darling, look.
[GRAY] What's up?
Did you find a way in?
Whoa! What in the
heck is that thing?
[LYON] Hmm...
[LYON] It looks like
an entrance to me.
[JUVIA] Going inside is our
only option at this point.
I will not allow it!
I forbid you scoundrels
from entering!
[JUVIA] But we'll have to
get past the guardian...!
[GRAY] That's just
great. Sorry...
[LYON] ...but we don't
have time to play with you!
[GRAY] Why didn't it work?
[LYON] Our magic has
no effect on him!
[GUARDIAN] You shall not
pass under my watchful eye!
[JUVIA] It's nullifying
their magic somehow!
[GRAY] Man,
this sucks!
[JUVIA] That glowing eye...
Maybe if I hit it...
[GRAY] So its eye
is its weakness?!
Good thinkin', Juvia!
[JUVIA] When he said
"under my watchful eye"
I figured that
had to be it!
[LYON] Look!
The door's opening!
Your brilliant plan
worked, Juvy!
Um... Please don't
ever call me that again!
C'mon, let's just
get inside, you guys.
[LYON] These are the
ruins of a church...
[GRAY] Hey look...
Isn't that Zentopia's emblem?
[JUVIA] What are those
floating rock cubes?
[LYON] They've got strange
markings on every side of them.
[GRAY] I think we're gonna
have a much better chance of
finding the clock
piece if we split up.
[LYON] I'll see what
I can find out here.
[GRAY] Okay, I'll go
take a look inside.
[gasps]
Are those arrows?
[LYON] There's
definitely something odd
about these rocks...
Let's see how this
will effect them.
[rock hitting rock]
[GRAY] What're
you doin'?
The arrows inscribed on the
rocks must mean something...
So I'm using my magic
power to move them.
[GRAY] What good
is that gonna do?
You care to explain?
Tell him, Juvy.
Uh, well... To be completely
honest, I don't--
Hey, I thought I told you
never to call me that again!
Oh no! Perhaps my lack
of formality has upset her.
Sorry...! Miss Juvy!
[GRAY] Would you two
knock it off already?!
Get serious!
My beloved Gray is in
a jealous rage...!
It just shows
how much he cares!
[GRAY] You guys are acting like
this is all fun and games...!
Now, figure out what we're
supposed to do with those rocks!
[JUVIA] Yes, of
course, sorry...
[LYON] Don't
yell at her!
Um... something seems
kind of odd about
the Zentopia emblem up there...
Does it look strange to you?
[GRAY] Hmm.
Now that you mention it,
it does look a little off.
I'm pretty sure
it's supposed to be
more of a diamond shape.
Yes, I think
you're right.
Hold on a minute...
And that does what?
If we move the
rocks like this...
We might be able
to open the door!
I get it now!
Well, it certainly took
you long enough, dimwit.
[GRAY] Did I do that right?
[LYON] Now let's try
applying our power
to all four of
the arrows at once.
[JUVIA] What's wrong?
Nothing happened.
[LYON] Give it
a second...
It worked...! And it's
all thanks to you, Juvia!
Are you proud of me,
my love?!
Is this light
or magic power?!
It's so bright!
You mean, we're still
not done with this thing?
[NATSU] Hey... Is
everybody all right?
[HAPPY] Aye...
[ROMEO] I'm still
alive somehow...
[LUCY groans] I thought
we were goners...
Wait, where's Michelle?!
[muffled screams]
[screams]
[NATSU] Okay, all
together now...! Ready...
[coughs]
[LUCY] You're not
hurt, are you?!
[MICHELLE] No... It appears
as though the entrance
was actually under the desert!
[LUCY] Yowza!
[NATSU] This one's same
as the other one...
It's been sealed
shut with magic.
[HAPPY] It doesn't even
have a keyhole anywhere.
[LUCY] Don't worry! This
kind of puzzle-solving
is right up my alley...!
All we have to do is
say the correct phrase
and it'll open up.
Let's try the
obvious first...
Open, sesame!
Why "sesame"?
I got no idea, kid.
[LUCY groans] No such luck...
I guess we're just gonna have
to yell out every phrase
we can think of until we
find something that works.
--[LUCY] Sesame seed! Sesame--
--[NATSU] Curry! Steak!--
--[HAPPY] Grilled fish! Stewed--
--[MICHELLE] Caviar! Truffle!--
Aren't you gonna
help out, Romeo?!
Umm...
Hey, Mr. Door...?
Would you please open up
for me and my friends?
[door slides open]
[HAPPY] Whaddya know? All
we had to do was ask it nicely.
[HAPPY] That's Zentopia's
emblem! I wonder why it's here.
[LUCY] It makes sense...! You
see, these ruins are known
as the Holy Tomb... It's one
of Zentopia's sacred sites.
It's been mentioned
in a ton of
their historical documents
and other church literature...
But its existence was never
proven, that is, until now!
[MICHELLE] Wait,
does that mean...?
We're the first people
to step foot in these ruins!
Oh, I get it...
So that's why those old
guys made such a big fuss.
[HAPPY] I don't blame 'em
'cause there's a good chance
we'll wreck the place...
Especially with Natsu.
[NATSU] Get off
my case, fur ball.
[door moves]
[HAPPY] The door closed!
[ROMEO] What're we gonna
do now?! We're locked in!
Don't worry,
I totally got this!
I read a lot of
adventure stories.
When the heroes
get stuck, they
do something like this!
What in the heck
is that gonna do?
[door moves]
[LUCY] Open secret doors!
[NATSU screams]
[HAPPY] What are those things?!
[ROMEO] Whoa...!
They're so creepy lookin'!
[LUCY] Yeah, no kidding...
[MICHELLE] I think
they're beautiful!
[HAPPY] Are you crazy?!
[NATSU] You led us
right into a trap, Lucy!
[HAPPY] The creepy faces
are gonna crush us!
[NATSU] Take this!
[LUCY] Stop, Natsu!
Ow-ow-ow!
Hot-hot! Ow...! Ow!
I told you to stop!
It seemed
like a good idea!
Oh, I know...!
Maybe if I just
turn this back...
Uh, where'd it go?!
Aw, man. That
was a close one...
How are we ever
going to get out of
this horrible place?
We just have to turn
this the opposite way...
I hope.
[NATSU] You sure it's
gonna be that easy?
[rumbling]
[NATSU] Uh-oh!
[ROMEO] Now they're
comin' from above?!
[LUCY] Oh crap!
[NATSU] We got no choice but to
get back in the noses again!
[HAPPY] Look!
We can't 'cause their noses
are closed up this time!
We need to think of
somethin' quick, you guys!
What're you doing?!
Escaping reality!
Is it time for
punishment yet?
[HAPPY] Hey, it's Virgo!
[ROMEO] Why is
she in a bikini?
When did you learn how
to summon two Spirits
at the same time?
"I didn't summon her!"
the lady says in
a panicked voice.
No, I came here of my
own accord because the Princess
is almost out of magic power.
[ROMEO] Okaaay... But why
are you wearin' a bikini?
[VIRGO] What's the matter? Don't
you like girls in bikinis?
[HOROLOGIUM] "Geez! Just make
a hole in the floor already!"
she exclaims impatiently.
Very well;
as you wish!
[explosion]
[HOROLOGIUM] "Why does
this keep happening?!"
she asks anxiously.
Where are we, darling?
I dunno...
I'm not even sure how
we ended up in this place.
It would appear that
this giant structure
is intended to be used
for teleportation.
[JUVIA] So many
floating arrow rocks...
Are we supposed
to pass through...
those gate things somehow?
I'd bet the clock piece
we're looking for is
at the end of them.
Maybe we can use
our power to make
a path outta these rocks!
It's worth a try.
[GRAY] Sweet!
It worked!
But I'd still love to get my
hands on whoever thought up
all this elaborate nonsense.
[Elvis impersonation] Uh-huh
[SUGARBOY] Hot dog!
It's Sugarboy!
You know it...!
The one and only!
[SUGARBOY] I knew I could
to get to the church on time,
but I'll tell you
what, getting in was
a whole other
story altogether...
But I'm not one for
crying in the chapel, baby.
So...
thanks for gettin' me in;
you may be shabby wizards
but you sure helped me out!
[LYON] I take it
he's the enemy?!
[GRAY] Sneaky bastard...!
You followed us in here,
didn't you?!
Aw c'mon, don't
be cruel, baby!
After all, I was
just doin' my job!
I've got no use
for you now that
I'm in Zentopia territory...
That clock piece is
as good as mine.
No! We won't
let that happen!!
[SUGARBOY] Spicy!
What a hard hearted woman!
How about I put on a
little show for you folks?
Y'all ready...?
Gonna be some good
rockin' tonight!
What in the hell?!
What is this stuff?!
Ew! It's so disgusting!
[GRAY] I didn't get the
chance to warn them...
He's trapped you
with his magic power!
Yeah! There's no escapin'
my "Dog Whistle" magic!
It's the tops, baby!
That's how I control my hound
dogs that got you all shook up!
[JUVIA] "Hound
dogs"...?! What?!
The show's over now!
Sugarboy...
is leavin' the building.
[GRAY] Hang on...! Once it's
frozen, I can shatter it
to get you out!
[LYON] Don't worry about us!
[JUVIA] Go after him while
you have the chance, my love!
Yeah... guess you're right.
[GRAY] But first,
I should tell you...
that slime gradually absorbs
your magic and physical power...
So please, be careful!
I told you not to worry.
This is nothing
that I can't handle... Remember,
we share the same master.
Good point.
[Elvis impersonation] Uh-huh.
So, you think you can
keep up with me, do ya...?
Good luck, Ice Boy!
[GRAY] Would you
cut the crap?!
Stop runnin' and come
fight me like a man!
When I'm done with you,
you're gonna wish that you
never messed with Fairy Tail!
[SUGARBOY] Uh-huh.
If ol' snow bird
was gonna catch up,
it's now or never...
Well, I guess he's
all hat and no cattle.
Hot dog...! I didn't
even see him comin', man!
[GRAY] It certainly
wasn't easy...
...but I caught up to you!
Uh-huh?
[SUGARBOY] So you noticed these
gates form one giant loop.
Impressive, Ice Boy.
[GRAY] It's not too
hard to figure out
if you just pay attention.
I guess if I want you
off my hide
I'll just have to settle
things once and for all!
I'm about to beat
the crap outta you...!
Just like in Edolas!
[GRAY] Is
that it?!
[SUGARBOY]
Sweet Lelani.
You're not gettin' your
hands on it... Hear me?!
Hey now, what you
strippin' for?!
[GRAY] Isn't
it obvious?!
Because...
I'm ready...
[SUGARBOY] Whoa, Jack, I don't
know how to respond to that
without things
gettin' real weird!
Huh?
[SUGARBOY] Hot dog,
now I'm all shook up...
What's... this feeling...
My heart can't seem
to stop... poundin'.
[GRAY] Huh?
Hold up...
Where is Virgo?
She's right
behind you...
[LUCY] What're you doing?
[HOROLOGIUM] "Is it
time for punishment?"
she asks expectantly.
[LUCY] No, uh...
I mean why are you
sitting inside Horologium?
[HOROLOGIUM]
"Because it calms me down,"
she says quite peacefully.
This place is even
weirder than the last one!
No kiddin'... Alright, let's
get a move on, everybody!
Princess...
I've finished repairing
this for you... Here.
You fixed the
Fleuve d'étoiles?!
Hang on... sorry...
but it looks like
an ordinary whip now...
It's far from
ordinary...
But I did make a few changes
to make it more functional.
[LUCY] That's awesome! Wow...!
I can't thank you enough!
Hey, is it just
me or does Lucy
live to crack the whip?
That's the kinda
character she is.
I'm within earshot,
ya know.
We should get
goin', Happy...
Aye, sir!
[NATSU] This sucks...!
I don't see a door anywhere.
Whoa, check out these
angry-lookin' statues!
I think those are
actually coffins.
[yells]
[HAPPY] All of 'em?!
[ROMEO] I betcha there's some
kinda trick to these, too.
[LUCY] I wanna touch them...
but considering what happened
to us last time...
I know that I
probably shouldn't,
but that only makes me want
to touch them even more...
Kinda weird.
[NATSU growls]
[screams]
What do you think
you're doin'?!
Oh, sorry...!
That statue just looked
so much like Gray
I just couldn't
help myself!
So much for
not touching...
[rumbling]
Why's the
ground shaking?
It feels like there
might be something
comin' this way...
Yeah, I knew
that would happen...
Guess it was smart of me
to bust it after all!
[ROMEO] Um...
I'm not so sure...
[mighty rumbling]
[LUCY] Definitely not
a smart move, Natsu!
Fire Dragon...
Brilliant Flame!
[screams]
[NATSU] I tried my best
but it didn't work!
[LUCY] When are you
ever gonna learn?!
[ROMEO] Are those bridges?
[HAPPY] Yeah,
there's three of 'em!
[MICHELLE] I have a feeling
only one of them is real...
[LUCY] We've got no way of
knowing which ones are fake...
What now?
[NATSU] We don't
have time to hesitate!
I pick right!
I pick left!
Maybe it's the
middle one?
Alrighty, Romeo!
You're the tiebreaker!
Uh... Well...
It's the middle one!
[NATSU] Let's go!
[MICHELLE screams]
[HAPPY] Romeo chose correctly!
[ROMEO] Look up ahead!
[MICHELLE] There's one
in front of us, too!
What should we
do now, Natsu?!
It's like we're stuck
in a pincer attack!
Listen up! We gotta jump the
balls right before they collide!
[LUCY] I can't jump that high!
There's gotta be
a way... Damn it!
[ROMEO] Hurry...
Happy, I need you
to pick up and carry
Lucy and Michelle, okay...?
Romeo, I want you to
grab my arm and hold on!
I can take care
of myself, Natsu!
Fine... You're on
your own, kiddo!
I don't mind
carrying Michelle but
Lucy's out of the question!
Watch it, flea bag!
[NATSU] Here they come!
[crash]
What'd I tell ya?!
I gotta admit that was
an impressive jump!
Aw yeah!
[HAPPY] Feels like my
right arm's gonna rip off!
[LUCY] Shut your yap!
[screams]
Hey Romeo...!
Grab somethin' with your magic!
Okay...! Here goes!
[MICHELLE] We're doomed!
[LUCY] Not if I can
help it...! It's time to see
what this thing can do...!
Let's go Fleuve d'étoiles!
[LUCY] Well that
was terrifying...
you guys okay over there?
[NATSU] Yeah... We're fine...
[ROMEO] Just a little sore...
Geez... How the heck are
we gonna get outta here?
[NATSU] Well, from
the looks of it...
we're gonna have to
work our way down.
[LUCY] That's a lot
easier said than done.
Go and fetch him,
my doggies...!
It's over, baby!
[GRAY] That's what
you think! Got ya!
Huh?
That's what I call spicy...!
Wait, I mean, chilly!
[GRAY] Ice Make: Floor!
Watch this!
I'm on fire, baby!
I got a fever
I can't control...!
Ya can't stop this
hunk'a burnin' love!
[GRAY] What in the-?!
What happened?!
They just vanished
into thin air!
Doubtful.
More like they went back
to wherever we came from.
Which means...
We need to try
and find a way
to jump into
that light, too!
On the other hand,
if we stay here...
I get to spend the rest
of my life with Miss Juvy.
That doesn't sound
so bad to me.
Well, it does to me!
Calm down...
I'm just joking.
Why am I feeling
so exhausted?
This magic must
be to blame.
No, I think
it's you...
Now... Time to break free!
I know that stance!
Not Iced Shell...!
Are you insane?!
No need to worry... I'm
merely releasing magic power.
Just be careful not to
get caught up in it!
[JUVIA] Oh, right!
You shattered it!
Let's go.
What's the matter?
[screams]
We have to catch
that light...!
So I can be reunited
with my love!
Well, it's
going this way.
[GRAY] Would you just give me
the clock piece already?!
[SUGARBOY] You really think I'm
gonna hand it over to you...?!
Please!
[GRAY] You'd better let
go of it right now...!
cuz If you don't I'm gonna...
Fall head over
heels... in love.
Whoa!
Yeah, baby...! A brown
eyed handsome man!
Where'd that
come from?!
Look, just so you know...
I'm not into guys!
Apparently your
heart is as frosty
as your biceps are bulging.
In that case, Ice Boy...
I'll force my
feelings on ya...!
Yeah...! I'm just a hunk...!
A hunk... of burnin' love!
[GRAY] Aw man...!
that's so hot!
[SUGARBOY] It's
spicy, ain't it...?
Just a lil' somethin' I picked
up from your pal Natsu...
You know, now that
I think about it,
he's kind of a
man's man, too.
[GRAY] I'll show you...!
This ain't nothin'...!
I can bust outta here!
Oh. That look...!
I like it!
Come on Ice Boy, let's boogie!
[LYON] Gray...! Haven't you had
enough of this buffoon...?!
How long are you going to let
him have his way with you?!
Get your act together...!
I won't have you bringing
shame to Ur!
[GRAY] No way
that's gonna happen!
It's got nothing
to do with Ur...!
And I would never do anything
to tarnish her reputation!
Gray, my love...!
Attack him now!
He's open!
Game over! Like I said,
when I'm done with you...
you're gonna wish you never
messed with Fairy Tail!
Whoa... man,
hot diggety...!
I'll be taking this with me.
Why...? Why...?!
C'mon, don't be cruel...!
Why do you have go on and check
me in to the Heartbreak Hotel?!
[ROMEO] Hey guys...
where are we?
[MICHELLE] It must be the
lowest level of the tomb.
[HAPPY] It looks
more like a city to me.
[LUCY] The monks who were
charged with guarding
Zentopia's Holy Tomb lived
their entire lives down here...
At least, according to
legend... Can you imagine
never stepping foot outside?
[NATSU] We've gotta find
a little clock piece
in a huge place like this?
[ROMEO] What's wrong? Can't
you just sniff it out, Natsu?
[NATSU] Nah, it's like
the clock hand...
For some reason,
I can't really smell it.
[gasps]
[sniffs]
Whoa... Hey...
Do you guys smell that...?
Where's it coming from?
Ugh.
I've got the chills...
Something feels wrong...
[gasps]
[LUCY] I hate being
right all the time...
♪
[HAPPY] Dontcha think
creepy places like this
are kinda exciting?
[NATSU] Yeah, yeah, but let's
not forget why we're here,
lil' buddy.
[HAPPY] Of course not!
We're here to explore.
[NATSU] No, man! Is this
some sort of game to you?
You'll get left behind
with that attitude.
[HAPPY] Wow, I'm not used
to you bein' so serious.
[NATSU] Well, that's the way
it's gotta be 'cause I want
our team to get it first!
[HAPPY] Ya see?
It really is a game!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
Footprints of the Myth!
This ain't a game...!
It's a competition!
[HAPPY] Same difference!
Whatever, let's get going.
Just follow along and
try not to get lost.
[NATSU] Huh...?! But
I thought I was the leader?!