[NATSU] I still have courage
because you're all here with me!
There's no reason to be afraid!
When we're together
we can accomplish anything!
[HADES] I shall send you
into the depths of darkness!
It's time for your sun to set...
Fairy Tail!
[blast]
♪
[HAPPY]
Daybreak on Tenrou Island!
Natsu!
Help...!
I'm gonna fall over the edge!
[WENDY] No way Lucy...
I've got you!
[HADES]
No...!
That's impossible!
My Arcane Magic
had no affect on you?!
How could that be...?!
My magic lies within-
[HADES]
They couldn't have...
[HADES] What have you
done to my heart?!
Look at that...!
All of the monsters
are starting to crumble!
[GRAY]
They're disintegrating!
[RUSTYROSE] The secret
behind Master Hades' incredible
magic power and longevity...
Lies within...
the demon heart
kept on our ship...
...known as the Devil's Heart.
[HADES]
If they destroy it...
I will lose all
of my magic power.
[KAIN]
Huh.
That's a weird sound.
[KAIN]
Whoa...!
I must be seein' things!
[WENDY]
Wow!
Is everything okay, Wendy?
You kiddin' me?!
[WENDY]
The Tenrou Tree...
[LUCY] How'd it go
back to normal?!
[ULTEAR]
Thanks to all of you...
I've been given
a new lease on life.
What's happening?
Our emblems are glowing!
Our magic power...
...it's back!
Well, it's about time!
[HADES]
How could I...
...the all-powerful Hades...
...be defeated by Makarov
and his children?
This is what you get
for hurtin' our master...
...you jerk!
[HADES]
Stay back!
[HADES] Until I stand above
all others who follow the path
of sorcery...
The devil within
me will never sleep!
[NATSU]
Laxus!
Attack...!
C'mon, Fairy Tail!
This might be our last
chance, so let's make it count!
We gotta blast this
geezer with everything we have!
If you come any closer
you shall feel my wrath!
We don't have
a contract yet, but...
Open!
Gate of the Sea-goat...!
Capricorn!
At your service, my lady...
Do you need aassistance?
Take him down!
Right!
How dare you...?!
I have rid myself of Sir Zordio!
I am now Lady
Lucy's Celestial Spirit...
[CAPRICORN]
Caaapricorn!
[WENDY]
I wanna get a hit in, too!
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
Ice Make...
Ice Bringer!
Requip!
Heaven's Wheel
[ERZA]
Pentagram Sword!
[HADES]
Grimoire...
Law!
Advanced Dragon
Slayer Secret...
Art!
[HADES]
No...!
I'm not going to make it!
Flame Lotus: Exploding...
Lightning Blade!
[Hades screams out]
[NATSU]
We did it, Gramps...
We showed 'em who's boss.
[NATSU] We put
everything on the line...
...and we showed 'em
the power of our guild.
[Natsu cries out]
[NATSU]
Fairy Tail...
...is the greatest!
I'm glad that's over.
Yeah.
So I guess...
this means we won, huh?
Here...
You might want this.
It is a little chilly.
Please...
help us!
You gotta save me, Natsu!
What is it now?
Who's that behind 'em?
Talk about bad timing.
Oh no...!
I'm completely drained
of magic power right now.
Me, too!
I'm afraid that I don't have
any power left either.
They all look
so angry, don't they?
[CARLA] Well yes,
but can you blame them?
Stay right where you are!
Hey, Gramps!
Everyone's here!
Master's better!
And so is Gahjeel!
Good to see you guys.
Indeed.
The Tenrou Tree has
returned to normal...
And So has its blessing
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120A]
There's more of them?!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120B]
Isn't that Makarov?!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120C]
Whoa! Look over there!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120D]
Master Hades!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120E]
He's been defeated!
[MAKAROV] I order you to get
off this island immediately!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120B]
Yes sir, right away!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120C]
Fire a signal flare!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 120D]
Sorry for all the trouble!
[FRIED] Something
troubling you, Gray?
Well, yeah...
Where's Juvia?
We don't know since she
never returned to base camp.
[Gray thinks] I hope she's
alright out there...
And what happened to Zeref?
[MAKAROV]
I'm proud of you for coming back
Is that what
you expected me to say?!
How dare you set foot on
Tenrou Island after I kicked you
out of the guild?!
What were you thinking?!
You're still expelled, y'know!
Geez, you're gonna
have a heart attack, old man.
Please try
to calm down, Master!
That's a big head!
[LEVY]
Shush, Lily!
It's Laxus?!
[BIXLOW]
You came back to us!
We thought
we'd never see you again!
Get off!
Even when he's hurt,
Master's strict as ever.
That's a real man for ya.
I guess so...
He'll have
a change of heart...
Watch.
Now...
...let's get back to the trial!
[HAPPY]
Are you kidding me?!!
The second round was
interrupted by Grimoire Heart
so it doesn't count!
I say we simplify things
and just have an all-out battle!
You must've been hit
in the head one too many times
if you think you stand
a chance against me when
you're all busted up like that!
[LEVY]
Chill out, Gajeel.
Whatever, it'll be a cinch!
'Cause I'm a
Lightning Flame Drag--
Hey, you alright?
Natsu!
Don't go passin'
out on me, ya wimp!
Fainting must be
a side effect of consuming
non-flame magic.
Anyway,
I think it's about time
we go back to base camp.
If we don't get some
rest soon our bodies won't
be able to hold up.
[ELFMAN]
You got a good point, lady cat.
[LISANNA]
Then Let's head back!
[LUCY]
Hey, wait!
Are you guys gonna
make me carry Natsu?!
Don't you worry, Lucy,
I'll be here to cheer you on!
So you'll cheer but
you won't help carry him?
[CAPRICORN]
May I be of assistance?
Please Allow me to
caaarry both of you, my lady.
Thank you, Capricorn...
I really appreciate your help.
[HAPPY] Natsu's getting' the
short end of the stick here!
Excuse me, Mr. Cat,
are you a guild-mate
of Lady Lucy's?
Aye, sir...!
I suppose you could say
that I'm her role model.
[CAPRICORN] Well in that case...
[CANA] What are the two of them
going on about back there?
[GRAY] I dunno but they seem
to be getting along great.
[CANA thinks]]
I hope my father's all right...
[GRAY thinks]
Juvia...
Makarov...
[HADES]
Why don't you finish me?
[MAKAROV]
Over the years...
I've learned
many things from you...
As thanks, I'm willing
to overlook what you've
done this time...
But you must leave
this island at once!
How can you
be so naïve, boy...?
If you let me live,
I shall return and when I do,
I'll crush your
guild completely.
You may have
defeated me in battle...
But you were
proven to be no match for
the children I've raised.
[HADES]
You're wrong...
I was weakened because
my heart was destroyed...
while those youngsters were
empowered by the Tenrou Tree...
It was merely a coincidence...
Otherwise, I never would have
lost to your "children"...
Never.
Why did you
fall to the dark side?
[HADES]
I told you once...
[HADES] Darkness is
the true nature of magic...
It is comprised of miracles
that were born in the shadows
and subsequently
brought into the light.
[HADES] After I retired
from Fairy Tail...
I began traveling down the
path of sorcery in the hopes of
learning the underlying
principles of the world.
[HADES] I learned that
the one we live in,
with its overflowing
magic, is a lie.
[HADES] The Grand Magic World
that Lord Zeref described
is the true world of magic.
[HADES] I wanted nothing more
than to see it for myself...
To make that happen,
I began collecting all of
the keys I needed to resurrect
the legendary black wizard.
[HADES]
I was so close...!
So incredibly close
to my dream...!
The primordial magic was
finally within my reach!
[MAKAROV] Even if your
dream had been realized,
it wouldn't change anything.
[MAKAROV] If magic's
true nature is darkness...
I can accept that.
[MAKAROV]
And if it's light...
I can accept that, too...
Because magic is alive...
So Its purpose is
ever-evolving with the times.
It grows, along
with the wizards who use it.
[MAKAROV] There's no definition
of magic because everyone
thinks of it differently...
It's as limitless
as your imagination...
It can become
darkness or light...
...depending on its caster.
[MAKAROV] Fairy Tail is free to
use magic however we choose.
[MAKAROV] These are all things I
learned from you, Master Precht.
[ELFMAN] How'm I supposed
to relax with Natsu
sawin' logs like that?!
Now, now, he needs
his rest as much as you.
[LISANNA] Hey, I just
thought of a great idea!
It's pigtail Natsu!
Isn't he the cutest?
That's So un-manly...
[HAPPY] I had no idea
that the thing we destroyed
was Hades' heart, did you?
Nope, it was
just a lucky break,
but we did a good job.
I suppose if you
could consider that
the ship's power source...
then the Exceed Squad completed
our mission exactly as planned.
That's true!
[HAPPY]
Aye, Sir!
[GAJEEL] Lily!
You ain't wounded are ya?!
Well, Not as bad
as you appear to be.
We missed ya, Laxus...!
Welcome back!
[TOMMEN A]
welcome back!
I think you're getting'
ahead of yourself there, pal.
I can't hold
back my tears of joy!
Come on...
[EVERGREEN]
Laxus...
You wouldn't believe all of the
terrible things that Elfman
did to me while you were gone!
Would you please punish him?
Why, You little-!
Oh, yeah...?
So when did you two hook up?
We didn't!
I mean, not like that!
It's kinda hard to explain!
What in the hell
is that supposed to mean?!
Excuse me, Lady Lucy...
I should really be going now.
I can't thank you enough
for all your help today.
I'll be counting
on you in the future.
And I, you...
I endeavor to become
your most vaaaluable Spirit.
[CAPRICORN]
By the way...
No, never mind...
Aw c'mon, there's no
reason for you to hold back,
just tell me!
[CAPRICORN]
In thaat case...
[CAPRICORN] While carrying
you earlier, I couldn't help
but notice you're
on the heavy side...
I think it would be a good idea
for you to lose some weight
to improve your health
and your maaaagic power...
If you'd like, I can help
you regulate your diet by
cutting down on faaaatty
meat and sweets.
On second thought,
maybe you should hold
back a little, okay?!
That was harsh.
Oh, wow...!
I feel so much better!!
You want me to take
care of your wounds next,?
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine...
You could probably
use some down time.
Nah...
I can't tell you how
amazing I feel now that
the Tenrou Tree's
back to normal.
[FRIED] I know I'm crying like
a baby but I can't help it!
[ERZA]
It's odd...
I don't understand how
the tree could come back
after being destroyed.
[GRAY]
Ultear...?
Nah, it couldn't be...
Someone's there!
Show yourself now!
It's just me!
Please don't attack!
Wait, Juvia?!
Geez, What happened
to you?!
I'm so sorry!
I tried to catch Zeref but he
ended up getting away from me!
Someone's gonna
have to punish me...!
C'mon, Gray...!
Go ahead and spank me
as much as you want...!
Please!
Thanks but no thanks!
I'm not really into that stuff!
[JUVIA] But I've
been a bad, bad girl!
[PANTHERLILY]
Okay, that's enough.
So all we're
missing is Gildarts...
Guess so...
I wouldn't worry...
I'm sure he's just fine.
[ELFMAN] C'mon Laxus,
be a real man!
[CANA]
Dad...
[GILDARTS] So let
me get this straight...
You screwed up so bad you got
expelled by your grandpa...?!
Man, you're so lame!
Well, I ain't half
as lame as you are!
There you are, Gildarts...!
Come and fight me--
You need your rest, kid.
He's out now.
[GRAY] Hey...!
No...!
Stop...! Please...!
Quit!
[GRAY] I already told you
I'm not into that kinda stuff!
Hey Wendy, can I
get a little help here?
You've gotta
wait your turn, Natsu.
Yeah, man up.
You can go next,
Lily, 'cause I'm more worried
about you than me.
Well, I don't see why,
because you're
the one who's covered in
bandages from head to toe.
Uh-oh, it looks
like you've got quite a line
forming now.
Oh, I don't mind at all...!
I'm just happy to be able
to help out somehow!
That's fine but
don't overdo it child.
[ERZA]
I can take over for you.
[WENDY]
You look amazing, Erza!
But why are you
dressed up like a nurse?!
[CARLA] Wait a minute; you
don't have any healing powers!
That's true, but
differences in ability
don't matter in battle...
It's our hearts
that will be tested.
Whaddya mean "battle"?!
Now look
what you've done!
You've scared the
poor girl half to death!
This can't end well...
[ERZA] All right gentlemen,
who's up next...?
If you'll tell me where it
hurts, I can decide whether
I should take your temperature
first or just go ahead and
give you an injection.
Does she really
think we're gonna fall for
the "hot nurse" routine?
We ain't that hard up.
Hey! What do you
think you're doin'?!
No cutting!
I'm the one who was
knockin' on death's door,
after all.
Stupid boys!
Aw c'mon, look on the
bright side Wendy, at least
you get to take a break
for a little while...
right?
Is it because she
has bigger boobs than I do?
It would appear that
tying bandages is much more
difficult than one might think.
Ow...!
Are you tryin' to kill us?!
[JUVIA]
I'm in shock...!
I can't believe I've been
begging Gray to punish me
and he's the one who
likes to be punished...!
I'm such an idiot!
Gajeel!
All of a sudden it feels
as though our battle
against Grimoire Heart...
...was in the distant past.
I'm afraid that
it always ends this way...
Yup, that's just how
things work in Fairy Tail!
[MIRAJANE] Master,
what do you wanna do
about the S-Class trial?
[MAKAROV]
Ah, good question!
I think we should head back to
the guild to clear our heads
a little bit before
we pick back up again.
Crazy...
I never would've
thought we'd be defeated...
Yeah...
Me neither...
I still can't
believe it's over.
Lord Zeref was there,
right before our very eyes...
We let the Grand Magic World
slip through our fingers!
Who goes there?!
Show yourself!
[ZEREF] It's people like you
who made me what I am today.
[ZEREF]
And, your wicked thoughts
that have summoned Acnologia.
This day shall forever
mark the end of the current era.
[ZEREF] It can no
longer be stopped...
This miserable
world will come to an end
here and now.
Lord Zeref...
♪
[NATSU] I was just
thinkin', I wonder how
that blockhead's doin'?
[HAPPY]
Which blockhead...?
Oh! The guy from the
Tower of Heaven?
What was his name again?
It was Wally, wasn't it?
[NATSU] Yeah, that's him
it's all comin' back to me now.
Remember how he was
all cool and, uh, blocky?
[HAPPY]
Yeah, I remember...
But what's bringing all these
memories back all of a sudden?
[NATSU]
A gut feelin'.
Next time: The Right to Love!
[HAPPY] Enough about
the past, the S-Class trial
is what's blocking
up my thoughts!
[NATSU] Good job
That was a great pun!
Ten points!
[HAPPY]
Cool...!
Wait, ten points outta what?