- HEY, GUYS.  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Lucy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL."
- Happy:
WE WENT ALL OUT ON OUR BATTLE
AGAINST THE PHANTOM LORD GUILD.
BUT THEY STILL
SNATCHED UP LUCY
AND MASTER LOST ALL
HIS MAGICAL POWER.
OH NO!
RESCUING LUCY
WASN'T AN EASY TASK,
BUT WE DID IT!
- 'CAUSE I--
I LOVE BEING IN FAIRY TAIL.
( cries )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Lucy: HIDDEN AWAY
IN MAGNOLIA'S EAST FOREST
YOU'LL FIND A TREE HOUSE
WHERE AN OLD FRIEND
OF MASTER MAKAROV LIVES.
PORLYUSICA IS
A HIGHLY SKILLED HEALER,
BUT SHE LIVES
A LIFE OF SECLUSION
BECAUSE OF HER
HATRED OF MANKIND.
HER SPECIALTY
IS IN THE TREATMENT
OF AILMENTS THAT WERE
CAUSED BY MAGIC.
WHICH IS WHY THE MASTER
HAS BEEN BROUGHT TO HER.
- WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
- HEY!  WE WANTED YOU
TO CURE OUR MASTER,
NOT MAKE HIM WORSE.
- IT'S WHAT HE DESERVES
FOR PUSHING HIMSELF
SO HARD AT HIS AGE.
HONESTLY,
YOU'RE SUCH AN OLD FOOL.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU SHOULD
BE LEAVING NOW?!
I'M SICK OF LOOKING AT YOU.
- WELL, CAN YOU AT LEAST
TELL US WHAT HIS CONDITION IS?
- WE WANT TO HELP YOU
TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- JUST GO HOME.
THOSE RIDICULOUSLY
WORRIED FACES OF YOURS
WILL ONLY AGGRAVATE
HIS CONDITION.
THESE SYMPTOMS SUGGEST
A POWERFUL WIND SPELL WAS USED.
MY GUESS,
THE SPELL KNOWN AS "DRAIN."
THIS TERRIBLE SPELL
DRAINS ITS VICTIM
OF ALL THEIR MAGIC ABILITIES.
THEIR POWERS THEN
DRIFT ALONG THE WINDS
UNTIL THEY HAVE
DISSIPATED COMPLETELY.
IF ONLY YOU'D GATHERED
MAKAROV'S POWERS
WHEN THEY WERE
INITIALLY DRAINED,
HE COULD HAVE
RECOVERED QUICKLY.
BUT AS THINGS STAND NOW,
IT'LL TAKE QUITE A BIT LONGER.
- HOW LONG DO YOU THINK?
- I'M SURE THE OTHERS
WILL WANT TO KNOW.
- WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE?!
- AHH!
- I'M SORRY, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU WERE TALKING TO US
ALL THIS TIME, MA'AM.
- OF COURSE I WASN'T!
I CAN'T STAND THE STINK OF YOU.
GET OUT OF HERE, ALREADY.
GO ON, MOVE IT.  SHOO SHOO!
- BYE, NOW.
- REAL NICE TALKING TO YOU.
- WAIT FOR ME!
- ( labored breathing )
- Porlyusica: YOU'VE ALWAYS
BEEN QUITE THE TROUBLEMAKER,
HAVEN'T YOU?
A WIZARD'S MAGIC
IS INTERTWINED
WITH THE VERY ESSENCE
OF HIS LIFE.
THE GREATER HIS POWER,
THE MORE DEVASTATING
THE DRAIN SPELL WILL BE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
FIGHT WITH ALL YOU'VE GOT
OR THIS MAY VERY WELL
BE YOUR DEATHBED.
YOU REALLY ARE SUCH
A PIG-HEADED OLD FOOL.
- ( Happy speaking )
- MAN, THIS STINKS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE HAD TO RETREAT.
- IT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
- WE SHOULD GO BACK.
WE HAVE TO GET REVENGE
FOR WHAT THEY DID TO LEVY.
- WE'LL MAKE THEM PAY!
- OKAY, SO THEIR
HEADQUARTERS IS HERE.
SO I'M THINKING WE SHOULD
TRY AND HIT THEM
WITH SOME LONG RANGE SPELLS
FROM THIS SOUTHEAST HILL.
- I'M BRINGING OUT ALL MY
EXPLOSIVE LACRIMAS NEXT TIME.
- HEY GUYS!  I'M GONNA
NEED SOME SPELL BOOKS
FOR A HOLDER-TYPE MAGIC
FROM THE ARCHIVES.
- DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL GET THEM BACK FOR THIS.
- ( sighs )
I KNOW.
I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
IT'S JUST...
ALL MY FAULT.
- BEING TARGETED
BY DANGEROUS PEOPLE
IS JUST ONE OF THE DOWNSIDES
OF BEING RICH.
AT LEAST YOU'RE PROTECTED
BY A REAL MAN LIKE ME.
- HEY, WOULD YOU
GIVE IT A REST ALREADY?
- I GOTTA SAY, I WAS SHOCKED
WHEN I HEARD THE NEWS.
WHY'D YOU HIDE
THE TRUTH FROM US, LUCY?
- I WASN'T TRYING
TO HIDE ANYTHING.
I MEAN, THERE'S NO WAY
TO BRING UP THE FACT
THAT I'M A RUNAWAY
IN CASUAL CONVERSATION.
I'VE BEEN GONE FOR A YEAR,
AND MY FATHER HASN'T CARED.
NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN HE WANTS
TO FORCE ME TO COME HOME?
HE'S DONE ALL THOSE
HORRIBLE THINGS
JUST TO GET ME TO GO BACK.
I HATE HIS GUTS!
STILL, IF I HADN'T
RUN AWAY IN THE FIRST PLACE,
NONE OF THIS WOULD
HAVE EVER HAPPENED.
- COME ON.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
YOUR DAD'S THE ONE TO BLAME.
- IDIOT.
- UH...
I MEAN,
IT'S PHANTOM'S FAULT.
- Lucy: NO.  I'M THE ONE WHO
BROUGHT TROUBLE TO THE GUILD,
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE
OF MY OWN SELFISH CHOICES.
I'M SO VERY SORRY.
I'M JUST GONNA GO BACK HOME,
AND HOPEFULLY ALL THIS
WILL BE OVER WITH.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I CAN'T SEE YOU PLAYING
THE PART OF THE PRETTY PRINCESS
SITTING AROUND
IN YOUR MANSION.
- LAUGHING WITH US
IN THIS FILTHY GUILD HALL,
GOING ON ADVENTURES EVEN THOUGH
YOU FREAK OUT ALL THE TIME,
THAT'S WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
- ( sighs )
- YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO STAY WITH US, RIGHT?
WHY WOULD YOU EVER GO BACK
TO THE PLACE YOU RAN AWAY FROM?
COME ON.
WHO ARE YOU TRYING TO KID?
YOU'RE LUCY OF FAIRY TAIL.
NO MORE RUNNING
'CAUSE YOU BELONG HERE WITH US.
- ( crying )
- AH, DON'T CRY.
IT'S JUST NOT LIKE YOU.
- YEAH, PLEASE. REAL MEN
ARE WEAK TO WOMANLY TEARS.
- SORRY.
- COME ON. I'M NOT
GETTING ANY KIND OF READ
ON WHERE MYSTOGAN IS.
- OH DEAR.
YOU DID YOUR BEST.
- IF LUCY'S THEIR REAL TARGET,
THEY'RE BOUND TO ATTACK,
AND I WOULD BET IT'S
SOONER THAN LATER.
RIGHT NOW WE'VE JUST
GOT TOO MANY WOUNDED
TO PUT UP MUCH OF A FIGHT.
- MASTER'S SERIOUSLY INJURED.
AND WE CAN'T SEEM TO
LOCATE MYSTOGAN.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE LEFT
THAT WE CAN TURN TO.
HELP US, LAXUS.
- ( groans )
- WE COULD REALLY
USE YOU ABOUT NOW.
FAIRY TAIL IS IN
TERRIBLE DANGER.
- MAN, MAKAROV IS FREAKING
PATHETIC. ( laughs )
I DON'T SEE HOW THIS IS
REMOTELY MY PROBLEM.
YOU'RE BIG GIRLS
SO DEAL WITH IT YOURSELVES.
- SO YOU'RE NOT
GONNA HELP US?
- OF COURSE NOT.
WHY WOULD I?
THAT SENILE OLD TOAD
STARTED THIS.
WHY DO I HAVE TO BE THE ONE
TO CLEAN UP HIS MESS?
- PLEASE, LAXUS.
PHANTOM'S TRYING
TO KIDNAP LUCY.
- WHO?
DO I EVEN KNOW HER?
OH WAIT.
IS IT THAT NEW GIRL?
I'LL TELL YOU WANT,
IF YOU CAN TALK BLONDIE
INTO BEING MY WOMAN,
I'LL DO ANYTHING SHE WANTS.
- YOU ARE SUCH A PIG!
- ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO TALK THAT WAY
TO A GUY YOU'RE
BEGGING TO HELP YOU?
DO ME A FAVOR, IF THAT GEEZER
MANAGES TO PULL THROUGH THIS,
TELL HIM HE'S OVER THE HILL AND
HE SHOULD HAND THE GUILD
OVER TO ME.
( laughs )
- ( crying )
- MIRA...
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW CAN SOMEONE IN FAIRY TAIL
BE SO HEARTLESS AND CRUEL?
I CAN'T JUST
SIT HERE AND WATCH.
I HAVE TO JOIN THE OTHERS
AND FIGHT.
- WAIT.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
- I FEEL TOTALLY USELESS BEING
STUCK HERE AT THE GUILD HALL.
I WANT TO HELP.
- I UNDERSTAND,
BUT YOU'LL ONLY GET
IN THE WAY AS YOU ARE NOW.
EVEN IF YOU WERE ONCE
AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
- Erza: THE MASTER'S
NOT HERE WITH US.
NEITHER ARE MYSTOGAN
AND LAXUS.
AND SO MANY
OF US ARE WOUNDED.
HOW COULD WE POSSIBLY
HANDLE ANOTHER BATTLE?
WHAT WAS I THINKING?!
WHY DIDN'T I GO WITH HIM?
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I'M A DISGRACE.
- ( crashing )
- ( gasps )
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- OUTSIDE!
- ( all exclaiming )
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- IT'S A GUILD HALL
WITH GINORMOUS LEGS!
- IS IT PHANTOM?
- ( all gasp )
- ( gasps )
- HOW DO WE FIGHT THAT THING?
- I NEVER ANTICIPATED THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'D GO TO SUCH EXTREMES
TO ATTACK US.
- THE MAGIC-FOCUSING CANNON,
JUPITER.
ENGAGE.
KILL THEM!
- All: YES, SIR!
- RUN!
GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
- ERZA!
- DON'T BE STUPID!
- SHE REQUIPPED.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- PROTECTING THE GUILD HALL.
- THAT'S HER ADAMANTINE ARMOR.
- IS SHE GONNA TRY TO
BLOCK THE CANNON'S SHOT?
- BUT THERE'S NO WAY
HER ARMOR'S GONNA HOLD UP
AGAINST A BLAST THAT STRONG.
- YOU'RE JUST RISKING YOUR LIFE.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
- JUST STAY BACK!
- ERZA!
- WE'RE NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO STOP HER.
WE JUST GOTTA
HAVE FAITH IN HER.
- ( gasps )
- NO!
- ( grunts )
( shouts )
AAH!
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
SHE ACTUALLY MANAGED
TO STOP IT.
- ONCE AGAIN, ERZA'S THE
MANLIEST ONE IN THE GUILD.
- YEAH, BUT LOOK.
- ( breathes heavily )
- YOU OKAY?
SAY SOMETHING.
- MAKAROV HAS FALLEN.
AND NOW ERZA CAN
NO LONGER STAND.
- ( exhales )
- Jose: ANY CHANCE OF VICTORY
HAS SLIPPED THROUGH
YOUR FINGERS.
SURRENDER LUCY HEARTFILIA
IMMEDIATELY.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
- THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
- LIKE ANY GUILD WOULD
HAND OVER ONE OF THEIR OWN
TO A MONSTER LIKE YOU.
- YOU HEAR THAT?
LUCY'S STAYING PUT.
- ( all cheering )
- I WON'T ASK AGAIN.
- ( crying )
- ( overlapping shouting )
- MAYBE I SHOULD
JUST GO WITH THEM.
GIVE MYSELF UP.
- WE WOULD NEVER
BETRAY HER LIKE THAT!
YOU'D HAVE TO
KILL US FIRST!
- All: YEAH!
- YOU CAN STOP ASKING NOW,
'CAUSE WE'RE NOT GONNA GIVE YOU
ANY OTHER ANSWER!
WE'RE TAKING EVERY ONE
OF YOU JERKS DOWN!
- ( all shouting )
- ( crying continues )
- ( groans )
IF DEATH IS WHAT YOU WANT,
I'LL GIVE YOU A SECOND HELPING
OF JUPITER!
YOU'VE GOT 15 MINUTES
TO PONDER THE FOLLY
OF YOUR ACTIONS!
- NO WAY.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- THEY'RE GONNA FIRE
AT US AGAIN?
- ( groans )
- ERZA...
- OH NO.  SHE'S OUT.
AND SHE'S THE ONLY REASON THE
REST OF US ARE STILL STANDING
AFTER THAT FIRST SHOT.
- OH NO.  IS HE REALLY GONNA
FIRE THE JUPITER CANNON AGAIN?
- HE'S KICKING US
WHILE WE'RE DOWN.
- YOU'RE IN QUITE
A QUANDARY
AREN'T YOU, FAIRY TAIL?
THERE ARE ONLY TWO WAYS
THIS SITUATION CAN PLAY OUT.
EITHER MY TROOPS WILL
TEAR YOU APART,
OR YOU'LL BE
BLOWN AWAY BY JUPITER.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
IF HE FIRES AT US,
HE'LL KILL HIS OWN MEN.
- SURELY HE'S BLUFFING.
WHO'D DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- NO, HE'S GONNA DO IT.
- ( both gasp )
- Cana: THOSE PHANTOM SOLDIERS
WERE CREATED BY
JOSE'S SHADE MAGIC.
THEY'RE NOT HUMAN,
SO IT WON'T MATTER TO HIM
IF THEY'RE DESTROYED.
- WHAT THE HECK ARE
PHANTOM SOLDIERS?
- YOU SAYING THEY'RE GHOSTS?
- WE'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
TO TAKE OUT THAT
JUPITER CANNON.
- I'M GONNA SMASH
THAT THING TO PIECES.
I ONLY GOT 15 MINUTES
TO WRECK IT, RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- COME ON, HAPPY.
- AYE, SIR!
- OKAY, ELFMAN,
WE'RE GONNA STORM THE PLACE TOO.
- OH YEAH!
- AND WE'RE GONNA STAY HERE
TO PROTECT THE GUILD HALL.
YOU WITH ME?
- All: YEAH!
- LUCY, COME WITH ME.
WE HAVE A HIDEOUT.
I WANT YOU TO STAY THERE
UNTIL THIS IS ALL OVER.
- NO.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT
THAT WE'RE IN THIS MESS.
I CAN'T JUST ABANDON EVERYONE
WHILE THEY'RE OUT THERE
FIGHTING FOR ME.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, LUCY.
I DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY,
AND NEITHER DOES ANYONE ELSE.
WE'RE NOT JUST
FIGHTING FOR YOU.
IT'S FOR ALL OF US.
IT'S FOR THE HONOR
OF OUR GUILD.
WE'RE PROUD TO
FIGHT THIS BATTLE,
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF US.
PLEASE JUST DO AS I SAY.
- ( gasps )
( sighs ) REEDUS,
TAKE HER TO THE HIDEOUT.
- OUI!
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU
TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
- OUI!
- I MAY NOT BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO JOIN THE OTHERS IN BATTLE,
BUT THERE ARE OTHER WAYS
I CAN HELP MY FRIENDS.
- ( screaming )
- Mirajane: THE JUPITER'S GONNA
FIRE AGAIN IN 14 MINUTES.
- YAH!
- Mirajane:
DON'T LET US DOWN, NATSU.
- AAH!
- YEE-HAW!
- BRING IT ON!
( grunts )
WHAT THE--?
I FEEL SO WEAK.
I CAN'T EVEN STAND.
- WAKABA!
MAN, WHAT THE HECK
ARE THESE THINGS?
- WHATEVER YOU DO,
JUST DON'T LET THEM TOUCH YOU.
- THAT IS CORRECT.
WITH A SINGLE TOUCH,
MY PHANTOM SOLDIERS
CAN WEAKEN YOUR LIFE FORCE.
SHADE MAGIC!
- SO WE JUST DON'T
TOUCH THEM, RIGHT?
- LET'S GIVE THEM
A TASTE OF WHAT WE DO.
- LOADING GUNS MAGIC!
SUNLIGHT SHOT!
SHOW THEM WHAT YOU GOT, BISCA.
- YEAH.
REQUIP GUNS!
YEE-HAW!
- ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
- NICE SHOOTING, LADY.
- AW, COME ON.
- THEY CAN REGENERATE?
- NOW WHAT?
- MAN, THAT JUST AIN'T FAIR.
- WE CAN'T SEEM
TO CATCH A BREAK.
- THERE'LL BE NO END TO THEM
IF WE FIGHT LIKE THIS.
WHAT'S THAT?
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- ( grunting )
CRAP, I'M BARELY EVEN
SCRATCHING THE SURFACE.
- I GUESS WE'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO DESTROY IT
FROM THE INSIDE, HUH?
- ( both grunt )
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO THIS.
- AYE!
- WHOA.
WHAT IS ALL OF THIS?
- Female Voice: 11 MINUTES
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- THEY MUST BE USING
THAT LACRIMA
TO COLLECT MAGIC ENERGY.
- YEAH, BUT WHY DO THEY
NEED ONE AS BIG AS THAT?
- 'CAUSE MAGIC-FOCUSING CANNONS
DON'T FIRE REGULAR AMMUNITION.
INSTEAD THEY FIRE
CONCENTRATED MAGICAL POWER.
- I DIDN'T GET MOST OF THAT,
BUT ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS DESTROY THAT THING,
DON'T WE?
- I CAN'T ALLOW THAT.
- IS HE A GUARD?
- Natsu: DOESN'T MATTER.
ANYONE WHO GETS IN MY WAY
IS GOING DOWN!
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- LIKE I CARE
WHAT YOU THINK.
NOW GET OUT OF MY WAY!
( grunts )
- NATSU,
WHY'D YOU HIT YOURSELF?
- I DIDN'T.
MY FIST JUST WENT CRAZY.
- IT SEEMS TO ME
YOU'RE GETTING IN
YOUR OWN WAY.
- Female Voice: 10 MINUTES
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- ( shouting )
- ( grunts )
( gasps )
THANKS FOR THE SAVE, CANA.
- YOU CAN'T LET THEM CATCH YOU
WITH YOUR GUARD DOWN.
WE NEED EVERYBODY ON THEIR
FEET TO FIGHT THESE GUYS.
THOSE HEARTLESS CREEPS
IN PHANTOM
DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW PAINFUL IT IS
TO WATCH YOUR FRIENDS FALL
OR HAVE YOUR GUILD HALL
DESTROYED.
WHATEVER WE DO,
WE CAN'T ALLOW THEM
TO TAKE FAIRY TAIL DOWN.
- ONLY NINE MINUTES UNTIL
JUPITER CAN FIRE AGAIN.
- MOVE IT, BUDDY.
I'VE GOT A CANNON TO DEMOLISH.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS
SHATTER THE GIANT LACRIMA
AND IT WON'T BE ABLE
TO FIRE ANYMORE.
- Totomaru: YOU CAN CERTAINLY
TRY, BUT I WON'T LET YOU.
- Female Voice: SEVEN MINUTES
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
SHUT UP AND LET ME
DO MY THING!
AAH!
( grunts )
- YOU OKAY?
- THAT HURT.
I DID IT AGAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- WHO CARES?
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH MORE TIME.
JUST FORGET ABOUT THIS GUY.
IT'S THE CANNON.
WE GOTTA BREAK IT RIGHT NOW!
- I'LL SHOW YOU.
- HEY, DID YOU HEAR
WHAT I SAID?
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- OH?
AAH.
( grunts )
- Female Voice: SIX MINUTES
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- I AM TOTOMARU,
AND I HAVE COMPLETE CONTROL
OVER THE ELEMENT OF FIRE.
- WAIT, I BET YOU'RE ONE OF
THOSE WHAT-CHA-MA-CALL-IT
FIVE GUYS, AREN'T YOU?
- JEEZ, THEY'RE CALLED
THE ELEMENT FOUR, NATSU!
HOW COULD YOU NOT EVEN
GET THE NUMBER PART RIGHT?
- YES.  AND ANY FORM
OF FIRE IS MY PLAYTHING
TO DO WITH AS I PLEASE.
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF IT'S NATURAL OR MAGIC.
ALL FIRE WILL YIELD ITSELF
TO MY COMMANDS ALONE.
- HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT YOU AIN'T CONTROLLING MINE!
- WOULD YOU QUIT
WASTING YOUR TIME
WITH THIS LOSER
AND START FOCUSING
ON HOW TO KEEP THAT
CANNON FROM FIRING?
- THIS ISN'T GOING TO
GO WELL FOR YOU,
MY DEAR FIRE WIZARD.
- HUH?
- ( chuckles )
- OH NO.  IT'S STARTING
TO ACTIVATE AGAIN.
- Female Voice: FIVE MINUTES
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- ( chuckles )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- MAN, THAT GUY WENT
AND PICKED A FIGHT WITH ME
FOR NO GOOD REASON.
IF HE WERE A REAL MAN,
HE'D KNOW YOU ONLY FIGHT
ABOUT STUFF
YOU TRULY CARE ABOUT.
- HOW FUNNY. THAT SOUNDED
JUST LIKE SOMETHING
ELFMAN WOULD SAY.
- YOU THINK? WANT TO SEE
MY IMPRESSION OF HIM?
( clears throat )
IF YOU WERE A REAL MAN--
OH MAN, HOW DOES HE GET
HIS VOICE TO GO SO LOW!
OH, NOW I'M GONNA HAVE ELFMAN'S
VOICE IN MY HEAD ALL DAY.
- Happy: YOU GOTTA MAN CRUSH
ON HIM, DON'T YOU?
- Natsu: NAH, I'M NOT
A BROMANCE KIND OF GUY.