[LUCY] It's been a busy five
days since Fairy Tail's rebirth.
It feels so good to be back
in my old place again!
I can't believe the
landlady had it open.
I could've moved into
the dorm with the girls,
or some other place, I guess.
Though...
I know I would've missed
the comforts of home,
and this amazing tub.
[LUCY] Things are actually
kinda starting to feel normal.
It's crazy to think
how much damage
the battle with Tartaros did.
The town was nearly destroyed.
But since the guild
was founded here
and has such a long
history with Magnolia,
everyone's welcomed us
back with open arms.
Just thinking about it
gives me the warm fuzzies.
[gasps]
[LUCY]
Just what I needed.
[giggles]
[BOTH]
Yo.
Are you serious right now?!
I'm serious about scarfin'...
I realize it's been a while,
but I need privacy!
Gotcha!
[gasps]
[screams]
[NATSU] You're gonna
have to train harder
to get a hit on me, ya know?
Let go!
Listen up.
We got a job!
Really? Uh! Hey!
[gasps]
[LUCY screams]
Not the job I hoped for.
Aw, stop your gripin'.
Since we're a guild again,
we need a guild hall.
Therefore, we're all
rebuilding that,
and our teamwork skills.
I'd like for Master
Makarov to notice both
once he finally returns.
Me, too. But is he
really coming back?
I'd bet my last jewel on it.
We'll wait, but Al and I
can track him if need be.
A bounty could work.
He's not a criminal!
And that's so cheap!
Wanna help?
How 'bout handin'
me those nails?
Of course! Here ya go, dear!
And now they'll rust.
[JET]
You hear about them?
They've been shacked
up this last year.
Well, what I heard is
they actually tied the knot.
And their union bore fruit!
I know, but what's even
more shocking to me
is that Lucy is his mistress!
No way!
And that fling with Erza.
Would you stop with all
those crazy stories?!
Besides, I'd describe it less
of a "shacking up" situation
and more of a "haunting."
[MACAO]
Okay...
[JUVIA gigggles]
How 'bout a cold one on me?
Thanks, Lisanna.
[LISANNA]
You guys thirsty?
Hooray!
Oh, yeah! Thank you!
[LISANNA]
Here!
A thirst‐quenching
liquid for me?
You know how to
sling some drinks!
Thank you!
It's because Mira and
I spent the last year
working at a
restaurant together!
Oh, please tell me that
Elfman worked there, too!
Manly meat!
He went away for training.
Didn't say what is was.
Just that it'd make
him a "real man."
'Zat so? I'll have to
test that out later.
I can show you right now
if you think you're
ready, pinky.
Not a great idea.
[NATSU chuckles]
Hey, Levy. What are you
working on over there?
Ugh. Filling out
lots of paperwork.
We can't just say we're a guild.
There's actually quite a bit
of documentation involved.
Without approval
from the council,
we'd be considered a dark guild.
That's true. And it's another
reason why we joined them.
We could learn the process
and make a couple of
friends on the inside.
Good strategy.
And once this stuff is done,
we'll be able to tell the world
Fairy Tail is officially back!
Thanks so much for
making this happen!
You're just the best!
[PANTHERLILY]
Now don't cry.
Okay. What am I gonna put
down for this last part?
That is a tough one.
Why's it hard?
Because we all need
to make a decision
about who our seventh
guild master will be.
You're right. Wow.
That is tough.
Is it though?
I have the experience!
Nobody wants that, Dad!
Let ol' Gildarts
have another shot?
We need a real master,
not some deadbeat dad
who comes and goes
whenever the hell he pleases!
It's a temporary measure
until our sixth master returns.
So anybody should suffice.
Well, almost anybody.
Maybe.
But I'm not sure we're even
the same guild we used to be.
[FAIRY TAIL yelling]
[yells]
[CANA] But we do need someone to
keep those knuckleheads in line
so crap like this
doesn't happen.
Oh, my.
[chuckles]
Pretty manly, man.
Be careful, okay?
Looks like they
both got stronger.
That's right Al.
So you'd better do something
about that pot‐belly.
[ALZACK gasps]
Daddy's gettin' flabby!
[ALZACK]
You think so?
[ALZACK groans]
Alrighty then!
[gasps]
[GRAY yells]
Not my darling!
You're a real man.
Get offa me!
Owie!
Ya want some too?
Hey now!
Jeez, guys.
You want some yummy raw fish?
I'm good.
Yeah! It's brawlin' time!
Let's wreck shop!
Sounds like a good idea to me!
I'm lusting for a good rumble!
I can't say it's
that surprising.
No it ain't. Warms my heart.
[ALZACK grunts]
Loke! I didn't summon you!
You're under arrest. All o' ya!
Oh, yeah!
One, two, pow! Kabam!
Crap, that stings.
You stupid jerks.
[MIRAJANE]
I'm happy for you, Elfman.
You felt so bad about
blowing up the guild hall,
but everyone knew it
really wasn't your fault.
You couldn't fix it.
So you had to get
stronger instead.
‐‐[WENDY screams]
‐‐[LUCY] Oh, no, Mira!
See what you've done?!
[bang]
Get back to work.
[FAIRY TAIL gasping]
[FAIRY TAIL]
Yes, ma'am.
[BOTH whimper]
[chuckles]
Well, that makes things
so much easier.
Our seventh guild master
will be... Erza Scarlet!
[FAIRY TAIL cheering]
Wait! Slow down, please!
Naming me as guild master?
I'm flattered, you guys, but‐‐
[MEST] You are the most
suited for the task.
Whoa! It's that guy!
Yeah, uh. That guy.
He seems familiar.
He does. I know he was
in the guild, but still...
Something's different.
And I can't remember his name...
[MEST] I've been waiting
for this moment.
I knew it would come and
we'd be together again.
Master Makarov is in trouble,
and you're the only
ones who can help him.
At least, I hope that's true.
[ERZA] I had no idea all of
this was under the guild hall.
[MEST] Yes. That's completely
by design, of course.
Tell me Doran‐‐or, Mest, rather.
Mest is my real identity.
Your memory is
likely still hazy.
That would be my fault.
Why didn't you let anybody
else come with us?
Definitely ruffled
Natsu's feathers.
[MEST] This is a sacred and
restricted place we've come to.
In fact, only guild masters are
supposed to know about it.
These are strange times.
That's the only reason I'm here.
[ERZA]
What is that?
[MEST] Fairy Tail's ultimate
secret, the Lumen Histoire.
[ERZA]
Master Mavis?
[NATSU]
Cut it out!
‐‐[GRAY] Stop pushing, ya dope!
‐‐[LUCY] Watch the hands!
[NATSU yells]
[ALL groaning]
Hey there.
What are you doing?
Seriously?
I literally said "only guild
masters were allowed."
It's very important that
we maintain its sanctity.
[NATSU] Whatever, we're
part of the guild, too!
[GRAY]
What is this anyway?
[WENDY] That's our
first master, isn't it?
[NATSU]
She's butt naked!
[LUCY] Yeah, so give her
some privacy, you creep!
Is that the first
master's body in there?
Is she still alive?
I don't understand this.
Why is she kept
inside that crystal?
What's going on here,
Mest? Explain.
I can't claim that I
understand it, either.
All I can say is
that it's something
extraordinarily important.
[NATSU] Aw, forget
about her right now!
Where is Gramps?!
"Forget about her"?
[BOTH gasp]
That's weird. It's like...
I can see something
What is this?
You're seeing my memories.
Beginning ten years ago.
You want me to
infiltrate the Council?
[MAKAROV] Yes. Because
you're the only one who can.
[MEST] So, what do
you want me to steal?
I'm not asking you
to steal something.
You'll be gathering their intel
on the western continent
and passing it to me.
[MEST] Yeah, that sounds
a lot like stealing.
Forget about covering up for
any of our prior "incidents."
Understood?
All I want is
everything they have
regarding the western
continent and nothing else.
May I ask why?
It's better that you
don't know the specifics.
But trust me, it's for
the safety of our family.
I won't fail you, I promise!
Here's an idea!
Oh, yeah! I'll erase
my own memory!
[MAKAROV]
That won't be necessary!
[MEST]
Since there's no real diplomacy
between the two continents,
I haven't been able to dig
up much info so far.
[MAKAROV]
I see.
But everyone here
has been very eager
to share their opinions
on Fairy Tail.
They hate us.
Yep. No surprise there.
Have you considered
reining in Natsu a bit?
Natsu's fine just
the way he is.
Are you sure?
[MAKAROV]
He's not the only reckless one.
After all, you volunteered
to erase your memory
to go undercover.
Yes, I did.
But you can lift and reinstate
the spell whenever you need to,
so I'll be fine.
You're certainly clever, Mest.
No doubt.
Thank you.
But while I'm still undercover I
need you to call me "Doranbolt."
[LAHAR]
Doranbolt,
there's someone here to see you.
[MEST]
A visitor?
Hello, sir.
May I ask what business
the master of Fairy Tail
has with me?
And by the way, did you visit
me last month as well?
[MAKAROV]
Ugh, this is such a pain.
[LAHAR]
Hey, Doranbolt. Makarov is here.
I wonder why Fairy Tail's
master would wana see me...
He visits quite often.
This gives me an idea.
Well, what is it?
I could use my memory
control magic to go undercover
inside that notorious
guild of troublemakers.
Okay.
[MEST] We'd surely get some
actionable intel that way.
We could, hopefully.
The first step is
planting a memory.
I can fool Makarov into thinking
that I'm a member of the guild.
I'll say my name is Mest.
That's a strange code name.
Oh, yeah! That's it!
I wanna know all of
Fairy Tail's dirty secrets!
Please stop.
And I'm guessing that was
how you wormed your way
into the S‐Class trial
on Tenrou Island,
before you ditched us there.
[GRAY, NATSU]
Not cool.
I'm deeply sorry about all that.
[ERZA]
Then what?
As you know,
seven years passed by.
It's been quite a while.
I'm so relieved to see you.
You're alive. Everybody's okay.
I must apologize;
I had no idea the mission
would last so long.
It's okay. I knew
the risks going in.
Look, Mest, it's all over now.
Come back to the guild.
You have a home with us.
[MEST]
Not yet.
After all these years,
I can't give up. I'm close.
The intel we've been looking
for is within reach.
[MAKAROV]
Huh?
[MEST]
But then, one year ago,
after the final battle
with Tartaros...
[MAKAROV]
Fairy Tail will not rebuild.
I'm disbanding it.
[MEST]
Huh?
[MAKAROV] Based on the
information you obtained
and my own personal
investigation,
I've come to realize this is
the only way we can survive.
It's to protect my children.
So all the work we've
done convinced you
to break up the guild?
It doesn't make any sense!
[MAKAROV] Whether you
agree with me or not,
the Alvarez Empire on
the western continent
is just too dangerous.
They pose a mortal
threat to us all.
Why are you so afraid of them?
The only noteworthy
thing they've ever done
is stage a failed invasion
of Ishgar over a decade ago!
Do you happen to know the
motive behind that invasion?
No.
[MAKAROV] They were after
the Lumen Histoire.
They traveled halfway
across Earthland
to obtain our most
sacred treasure.
I assume you don't
know how that ended.
The invasion didn't fail.
It was abandoned after the
Council flexed its muscles
in the form of a
terrifying weapon.
[MEST]
The Etherion.
We just learned about the
magic‐nullifying system, FACE.
This, too, was a major part
of the Council's arsenal.
Alvarez simply could not
afford the risk involved.
However, those council
members have been wiped out,
and both the Etherion Cannon
and the FACE system
have been destroyed.
So what does that all mean?
It means Ishgar has lost every
tool we had to deter Alvarez.
[MAKAROV]
Mm‐hm.
There's no doubt in my mind
they will invade again.
[MEST]
I still don't understand
why we would have to
break up the guild.
Someone hits us, we hit back!
That's the Fairy
Tail way, right?
[MAKAROV] The only viable
option we have now
is to disband the guild.
Why?
[MAKAROV] Including Fairy Tail,
the continent of Ishgar is home
to 500 wizard guilds,
give or take.
However, at its peak,
the western continent
had around 730.
That's counting official,
legal guilds and dark guilds.
But the Alvarez Magic Empire
was able to unite
all of those disparate
groups under one banner.
And now they possess a
military power without equal.
We'd have no chance
of stopping them.
[gasps]
Although it's true
that our ragtag guild
has bested many powerful
enemies over the years,
this is quite different.
No one we've faced has been
even close to this level.
Master! What can we do?
[MAKAROV]
I'm going to the Alvarez Empire
to negotiate with them.
If I can't dissuade
them from invading,
I'll buy us some extra time
by threatening to activate
the Lumen Histoire.
They understand its power.
[MEST]
Are you serious?
Admittedly,
my chances are slim,
but they'd be better if you
could rebuild the Magic Council.
Wait! There has to
be some other way!
[MAKAROV] I fear that if
something were to happen to me
while Fairy Tail still existed,
my children would
be the next targets.
I cannot put them in harm's way!
I've no choice!
I'm willing to forfeit
our standing.
Throw away our glory.
If that can guarantee the safety
of our family, so be it!
[MEST] Master, please
think this through.
Because trying to hold back
an entire nation by yourself...
This is a suicide mission!
I'm carrying the lives of
my children on my shoulders!
And that is what it
means to be a parent.
[NATSU]
Okay!
So Gramps went over to deal
with this empire or whatever
and he never came back?
He wanted to protect us.
Disbanding the guild was
the only way he could.
One whole year... and
not a word from him.
Nothing.
[HAPPY]
Why didn't you try to stop him?
You do know Master Makarov
is impossibly hard‐headed.
What could Mest have done?
Do you think he's okay?
I don't know what to think.
Hopefully, he's still
in negotiations.
But they could have
imprisoned him. Or worse.
[ERZA]
My heart tells me he's alive!
So what'd you do?
I started following
Mokarov's plan.
And I got to work on re‐forming
the Magic Council.
With some help from Warrod,
I assembled a new council.
This one including the Wizard
Saints as core members.
We'd talked about this
back at Lamia Scale.
I knew the council had
been looking for him,
but Lyon just said they
were concerned.
[MEST] Warrod does know
how grave the situation is,
but I'm not so sure
about the others.
Regardless, the entire
council agrees
that Alvarez poses a
threat to all of us.
They were able to establish
a line of defense,
and it seems to have deterred
any invasion or attack so far.
That tells me Gramps managed
to buy us some time,
just like he said.
Ya know? So why the hell
isn't he back yet?
[MEST]
I can't say for sure.
Word travels slowly. He may not
know the new Council exists.
Or perhaps they're
keeping him there.
You realize we gotta
go save him. Don't ya?
I know.
I did as he said up till now
and got the Council
back and running.
But I'm in Fairy Tail,
so it's time I start to
break the rules a little.
[HAPPY] Now that we have
the guild back together,
no one's gonna stand in our way.
Am I right?
We'll bring him back home!
Hold on!
Remember what Master told him,
this is an unbeatable enemy.
We can't act on impulse.
Erza.
We've gotten way stronger
over the last year!
Do you really believe that
these jerks can beat us?
Master risked his life
and legacy to save ours.
He sacrificed everything.
We must honor his gift.
[ERZA] We'll do that by
rebuilding the guild hall,
taking jobs again, and restoring
Fairy Tail to its former glory.
We're finally reunited.
We need to enjoy this moment
of happiness together.
As the new master, these
are my top priorities.
We're not going?
Really? Come on!
[ERZA]
However,
my feelings as a fellow member
of the guild are different.
We have no other choice
but to bring Makarov home,
and quickly.
Which means... only those in
this room will join the mission.
A small team works best.
We'll infiltrate Alvarez,
rescue our master,
and make our escape.
This will not be
an all‐out war.
Hear me? We need focus.
That means we won't be starting
any unnecessary fights.
Am I clear?
Yeah, sure.
Let's do it you guys!
Gramps is counting on us!
Ha. Beat us to the punch.
What are you talking about?
They're gonna go with a
small team invasion strategy?
Alrighty then.
So we'll have to give a
different approach a try.
Hey, Cana.
Do you happen to know
where Gray wandered off to?
I drank that cool drink
right up! And it was good!
How could you do such a thing?!
Are you in there?!
Answer me, Gray!
[MIRAJANE]
If you're looking for Gray,
I saw him following Erza
and Mest a while ago.
I think he was with
Natsu and Lucy.
[JUVIA]
What?
Did you say Lucy, too?
[GRAY]
My, where could everybody be?
[LUCY] Who cares? All that
matters is you're here.
[LUCY, GRAY gasp]
[GRAY]
Lucy.
[LUCY]
Gray.
[GRAY]
Oh!
[groans]
That kinda hurt.
Hey there. You wanna
take a little tipple?
I'm gonna put the
B Team back together.
The B Team?
Like our team from
the Grand Magic Games?
We're gonna look for
ol' blond lightning, too.
[JUVIA]
Hm?
Wait, lightning? Where?
What are you talking about?
Gajeel, do you know
where Laxus is?
[chuckles]
[LUCY] Master Makarov is being
held inside the Alvarez Empire,
and it's up to us to
get him outta there.
We're gonna need a
foolproof plan to save him.
So it's off to the
western continent,
where the mysterious
empire is headquartered.
But first, we'll need to make a
little stop on Caracol Island.
Instead of getting our
second wind, though,
we run into an
explosive situation!
Next Time: "Law of Space."
He who controls space,
controls our progress.