[LUCY] What the--?
Oh yeah! Water!
That's all I need!
Oh no!
Lucy's about to summon
the fish-lady spirit!
I thought
you liked fish!
[LUCY] Open, Gate
of the Water Bearer!
Huh?
[LUCY] Aquarius!
[AQUARIUS growls]
[MIRAJANE grunts]
[KAMIKA] Oh dear. It seems
the tales I'd heard about you
were nothing
more than that.
Mirajane,
the She-Devil?
Just a silly fantasy.
But I can
still have fun.
Executing criminals never fails
to bring a smile to my face.
[KAMIKA] Paper Blizzard:
Purple Dance!
I'm sure you remember
what these papers can do.
[MIRAJANE] Well, if you're
talking about making
it hard for me to
move. I remember.
Good. But, we can still
have so much fun together.
[KAMIKA] Paper Blizzard:
Red Dance!
I forgot that she
could use fire magic!
Now there's the
look I wanted to see.
That beautiful
face of yours
is even lovelier with
that expression...
I can see all the pain and
fear you're feeling inside.
It sends so many
shivers down my spine!
[KAMIKA laughs]
[MIRAJANE grunts]
[KAMIKA] But I suppose it's
time to cool you down a bit.
Paper Blizzard:
White Dance!
[MIRAJANE] My body feels
like it's turning to ice!
[KAMIKA] Oh, this is
unbelievably satisfying.
But I want more.
Let's liven things up!
[KAMIKA] Paper Blizzard:
Yellow Dance!
Yellow papers hold
the spirit of lightning.
]You may
use lightning.
But this is nothing compared
to what Laxus can do with it!
So you'd
like more pain?
Then perhaps I can
give you a taste
of what true agony feels like.
[KAMIKA] Paper Blizzard:
Green Dance.
[MIRAJANE] What is this?!
It's an entirely
new level of pain.
These papers hold
the spirit of poison.
It should feel like a
million burning needles
are racing through
your bloodstream!
[MIRAJANE] You get some
sick enjoyment out of this?
[KAMIKA] What a silly question!
Of course I enjoy bringing
criminals to justice!
Besides, you
chose your fate
when you broke the
laws of the kingdom!
It's quite an
intense pain, isn't it?
But still, you seem
to be withstanding it.
Could it be your
S-Class background?
I suppose I was a bit
too stingy with the poison.
[KAMIKA] Green Dance, Level Two!
[MIRAJANE grunts]
[KAMIKA] Ah,
that's more like it!
So, are you prepared to die?
[MIRAJANE] This is wrong.
Magic shouldn't be
used to kill people.
But sometimes, you
have to go to extremes
to protect others.
If you have the
power, you must use it.
To do what
has to be done.
[KAMIKA] Nothing but
complete and utter nonsense.
It appears the poison
has made you delirious!
[HAPPY] Our Place!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon... Roar!
What the...?
Where did all my fire go?
[LEADER] Neutralized.
My right scythe
reaps criminals' heads,
and my left scythe
reaps their magic.
Breathe all
the fire you wish.
The result will be the same.
Just hot air and the sound
of your life escaping.
[NATSU] Man, you love to listen
to yourself talk, don'cha?
So magic doesn't work on you.
That just means I'll
have to pound your face in!
[PANTHERLILY grunts]
[NEPPA] Sploosh!
[NEPPA laughs]
You're pretty tough.
I didn't think
skinning a pussy-cat
was gonna be so much fun!
Here kitty-kitty!
[PANTHERLILY] I'm no
pussycat! I'm an Exceed!
[NEPPA] I don't
care what you are.
But it seems like you
may have had some kind
of military training
or something?
As a matter
of fact, I have!
Guess that's what
makes you so hard-headed.
But I can wash that all
away with a little splash
of my special blend!
[PANTHERLILY] Never!
[NEPPA] Pop!
[NEPPA] Sploosh!
You sure are a nervous little
pussycat, aren't ya now?!
[NEPPA] Well ain't
that something?!
I thought my magic acid
could eat through anything.
Guess not!
[NEPPA laughs]
[NEPPA] Cuz' there you are,
back on your feet again!
I sure do love
me a challenge!
All your talking
just lets me know
how weak you are!
Oh yeah?
[PANTHERLILY] It's obvious...
A fighter who brags on
and on about his skills
when he should be
showing them off.
is simply covering
for his insecurities.
[NEPPA] Is that why ya keep
on flapping your gums, kitty?
[PANTHERLILY] I'd be willing to
bet that the only things you can
dissolve are those without
a mind of their own.
That you can only kill
what is weaker than you.
A true warrior
doesn't work that way.
That's why I won't lose.
[NEPPA] Oh?
That's a nice little speech,
but it ain't gonna help you.
In fact, you just
made things worse!
I'm done playing around with
you! It's killin' time!
[HAPPY] Oh no! It's
the mean ol' fish lady!
[CARLA] Hush, Happy!
If you got something
nasty to say about me...
Just say it! 'Kay?!
[HAPPY] She's so scary.
[CARLA] Then stop provoking
her, silly tomcat.
[UOSUKE] Boy howdy, that
is one funky lookin' catch!
[LUCY] C'mon Aquarius,
take this guy out for me!
[AQUARIUS] Tch...
Hey, where is this
attitude coming from?
I thought we were past all that.
Well, we're not.
Ya know...
I'm not feeling it today,
see ya later.
[LUCY] No, please don't go!
So, um... What's the matter?
Are you and Scorpio
having some issues?
Say what?!
[LUCY screams]
Do you know about
something that I don't?!
'Cause if I find out you're
keeping secrets from me,
you won't live to
regret it, bimbo!
No, I promise!
It's just that he seemed kinda
off when I summoned him earlier.
He's normally so cool and stuff,
but he wouldn't even look at me.
Does he normally
make eyes at you?
Is there something
going on behind my back?
No, no, there's
absolutely nothing going on.
I actually like living
too much to piss you off.
Quit jawbonin' cuz
we got some executin' to do...
Ya hear me?!
[AQUARIUS] I don't
like being interrupted.
You hear ME?!
[LUCY whimpers]
[UOSUKE] Doggone?!
That Whirlpool was a real doozy,
and you just sucked
the dang thing up!
[AQUARIUS] If you
wanna know the truth,
apparently Scorpio went on
a date with some other girl.
What? Oh, no he didn't!
[AQUARIUS] Apparently,
someone even saw them.
Apparently, huh?
Taurus said he thought
he heard Crux mumbling
something about
Nicola or somebody
seeing him out somewhere.
He said that he was slinking
around with some cheap floozy
in the human world.
Have you tried just
asking Scorpio about it?
It's not
that easy.
When I talk to him I start
to get all giddy and stuff.
So... I really just
don't see that happening.
Well, do you want
me to talk to him?
If you think this is
some kinda joke,
you're dead wrong!
You dare say one word
to him about this
and I'm gonna make you
wish you were never born!
[LUCY] Okay, mum's the word.
This is more entertaining
than I expected.
It's way better
than being stuck
in the middle of a fight.
[UOSUKE] Meddlin' in
a lady's love life
is like swimmin' with sharks.
You're gonna get bit...
Hang on, that reminds me...
[LUCY] What the? Oh yeah!
Water! That's all I need!
So this here water's
what let her land
that crabby fish lady, huh?
And that means...
If there wasn't no
cold water around,
then she wouldn't
be around, neither.
[HAPPY] Lucy! Look!
He's got some super weird
grin for some reason!
Careful, I think he's figured
out his plan of attack!
Terrain Effect Magic:
Boiling Water Zone!
[LUCY] Hey.
This water is getting
really hot all of a sudden.
[CARLA] It's steaming!
[HAPPY] Nice! It's a hot spring!
[LUCY] Oww! Hot! Hot!
[UOSUKE] Oh, that hot water's
got my little catch a-jumpin'!
Things are gonna get
really heated up now.
I'm just about
ready to reel ya in!
Yeah. This is
gonna be really bad.
[COSMOS] ♪ A beautiful sleep,
full of beautiful nightmares! ♪
♪ La-la-la la-la! ♪
♪ So much blood to
feed the flowers! ♪
[WENDY] Is that a song?
Yeah, And I wrote
it all by myself!
[COSMOS gasps]
[COSMOS] Wait, how did
you get up from that?!
[WENDY] Oh, shining light.
Cleanse me of my ailments...
Re-Rays.
[COSMOS] What?! Impossible!
Your status
ailment spells
will never be
able to work on me.
Because my friends all count
on me to support them.
]But still...
sometimes supporting
isn't enough.
What's happening?
This wind... it's
scattering my lovely flowers!
When I fight.
I become a Sky Dragon!
No! How revolting!
[COSMOS] Running
away isn't beautiful!
And playing dirty tricks
on me is disgusting!
I thought you had true beauty
underneath all your sins.
But there is
nothing but ugliness!
I haven't done anything
[COSMOS] I can
never forgive you.
I can never love you...
[WENDY] Who said
anything about love?
[COSMOS] I will reduce your body
to ashes scattering in the wind!
Spore Bomb...
Rinka Renka!
[WENDY shouts]
[COSMOS giggles]
When this dance is over,
you'll be just a memory...
with not even bones to bury.
[WENDY grunting]
[LEADER] You're only
postponing the inevitable.
Your fire magic is useless,
and your attacks have not
even come close to me.
[NATSU] Yeah, it's
kinda annoying...
But like I was saying, I'll
just have to kick your butt
the old fashioned way.
[LEADER] For your hubris,
and your crimes,
you will pay with your head.
[NATSU] Listen pal, I've had
more than my fair share
of fights where I
didn't use magic.
So I ain't scared
of you at all.
I'm not gonna
lose to a guy like you.
'Cause I've got some
other scores to settle
when we're done here.
[LEADER] You guild wizards
are ridiculous.
I won't deny that
you're strong...
But you will still fall before
me like all the other criminals!
And like them, you'll
become a nameless corpse!
[NATSU] I don't think so!
Gimme a shot! 'Cause
I'm fired up now!
I wish we could
help Natsu and them.
but master told us that we
shouldn't leave the coliseum.
Well, he's
right about that.
We don't wanna attract
any unwarranted attention.
If someone gets
suspicious it could
put Lucy's rescue
mission in trouble.
Oh, hey.
You ladies run off
to grab a snack?
[KINANA] Yeah, and walk
off some nerves, too.
[MAX] Tell me about it.
I'm worried about
Natsu and Lucy.
And the games are making
me even more stressed out.
[LAKI] Where'd Warren go?
I haven't seen him
in a little while.
[MAX] Somethin' was gettin'
in the way of his telepathy...
So he was gonna try to
get up onto higher ground
to see if that helps.
[KINANA] I'd love to get
outta here, but we can't...
It feels so helpless,
just waiting.
[LAKI] It'll work out.
You know Natsu...
I'll bet he's probably on
his way back with Lucy.
And the match seems
to be going our way,
exactly like Master Mavis
said that it would.
But there still are a lot
of tough ones left to beat.
Just have faith in her plan
and we'll win the games,
and have everybody
back to celebrate.
[ELFMAN] I'm a man!
[MAX] Yeah, nobody
said that you weren't!
Help me talk
some sense into him!
I'm making
perfect sense.
What's the matter?
Mira went with the team
that was going after Lucy..
We shoulda heard something
from them by now!
So, this genius thinks
that we all need to go
off and storm the royal palace
so we can go help them fight!
[MAX] Not exactly the best idea.
[ELFMAN] I know Mira can
hold her own but I'm worried,
and a real man fights
to save his family.
[LISANNA] We all want to help
them, but we just have to
give it some time
for the plan to work!
Got no other choice.
Besides, she's with Natsu
and he won't let anything
bad happen to her.
Well. As long as he
doesn't do something crazy
and stray away
from the plan.
That's it! I'm going!
No, you're not!
Just try to relax, man...
Natsu went through that whole
"second origin" thing...
And we all just saw
him beat the crap
out of those guys
from Sabertooth.
Mirajane has
her Satan Soul forms,
and Wendy is a
Dragon Slayer, too...
We'd just get in their way.
You're absolutely right.
We should focus our
energy on our team spirit
and cheer for our
guys in the match.
All right... I guess
I could pound some sense
into that old geezer
Darton, instead.
Were you
even listening?
You're staying with us!
We should probably
get back to our seats...
Somebody could be
watching us right now.
You're right. Come
on, let's get moving.
[ELFMAN] Yeah, okay... But
I still don't like this.
A real man would do
something, ya know?
I know, but
that's how it is.
Mirajane can handle it.
Actually the
real truth is...
we should feel sorry for the
poor soul who tries to stop her.
Impossible. You should
be so full of poison by now
that your body feels like it's
burning from the inside out!
You should
be on your knees.
screaming in pain
and begging me to put
you out of your misery!
How in the hell can
you still be standing up?!
[MIRAJANE] That's easy.
There are so many things
that you don't know about me.
Like, when I know
that I'm being watched...
or anywhere around
people, really.
I tend to stay a little guarded.
I try not to go all
out strength-wise,
because I don't
wanna scare anybody.
What?
[MIRAJANE] It's funny.
I'm a walking
contradiction, I guess.
But it's just the way I am.
Always have been.
But whenever it's just me,
I can go full-throttle
one hundred percent
power, no
problem at all.
What exactly are
you trying to say?
[KAMIKA gasps]
[KAMIKA] Unbelievable!
Is she really inhaling it?!
[MIRAJANE chuckles]
[MIRAJANE] Demons
like me love poison.
It's actually one of
my very favorite things.
A disgusting
Take-Over spell...
But I suppose it's fitting for
a filthy criminal like you!
It's over!
Because I can still
leave you paralyzed!
[KAMIKA] The gray papers
hold the spirit of protection!
[MIRAJANE] You may
be an executioner...
but just how much
of a fighter are you
when your victim
can fight back?!
[KAMIKA] The blue papers hold
the spirit of divine winds!
[MIRAJANE] Oh? The "divine"
running away from the demonic?
Not this time.
[KAMIKA] She can fly?!
[MIRAJANE] I'll ask
you once again!
[KAMIKA grunts]
[MIRAJANE] Can you tell
me where my friends went
or is this gonna get ugly?
[KAMIKA coughing]
I don't have to tell you
anything I don't want to!
[MIRAJANE] How far
are you willing to go
to keep it from me?!
Because, I'm
ready to fight you
without holding anything back...
So you'd better give me
the answer I'm looking for.
You're an
unclean monster!
[MIRAJANE] I'm a She-devil!
[KAMIKA] The black papers
hold the spirit of cleansing!
I can defeat a devil!
All I have to do is
purge your darkness!
[KAMIKA gasps]
My darkness is a flame
that'll never go out!
She's gone!
[KAMIKA grunts]
[KAMIKA] The indigo papers
hold the spirit of love.
Meaning they'll
conjure up any pain
you've endured
grieving over love!
And your heart will
literally be broken!
[roaring]
[LISANNA] C'mon.
Don't be afraid, Big Brother.
We still love you.
[MIRAJANE] Lisanna!
You have to wake up, Lisanna!
[rain pouring]
[KAMIKA] Now you'll be
trapped in your misery.
Forced to relive the trauma
and go through the pain
over and over again.
An endless hell.
The grief will
keep intensifying
until you lose your mind.
Ah...
[MIRAJANE] I got over
that pain a long time ago...
I know that I'm one of the
lucky ones, but I'm not alone...
Everyone experiences
profound pain
at some point
in their life.
But they
can all heal.
Let the past fade
into their memory.
For me, magic
gives me the strength
I need to grow from it.
Stop all this babbling!
I won't be lectured
by a criminal like--
[KAMIKA muffled screams]
[MIRAJANE] I learned
how to use my power
to protect the
people I care about.
Let me show you.
[KAMIKA whimpers]
[LUCY wails]
This water is boiling!
That means Aquarius
can't use it to attack.
What are we gonna do?
[UOSUKE] Yeah, she's
right on the money.
So, why don't ya haul it on
outta here, ya old rotten fish!
You're all used up,
and I guarantee
if I was your boyfriend,
I woulda thrown ya back too!
[LUCY] What a low blow!
What?!
I don't think he
shoulda said all that!
Definitely not.
[AQUARIUS] Water temperature
doesn't make a bit of difference
to me. This idiot
even summoned me
in the middle of
her bath before.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. That was
not such a good time.
Kinda blocked it out.
[UOSUKE] I was sure
that was gonna work!
What a load of chum!
[LUCY] Now, let's teach
this jerk a lesson!
Why don't
we just kill him?!
[PANTHERLILY grunts]
[NEPPA] You got popped!
There's never been a criminal
that's been able to get away
from my Multi-Angle acid
technique, so say your prayers!
[PANTHERLILY] Dig deep...
I won't be able to stay in
combat mode for much longer.
Gotta
make it count!
[GAJEEL] Come on! Is
that all ya got!
Step it up!
[PANTHERLILY thinking]
All those days I spent
training with Gajeel.
I gotta remember them.
[grunting]
[GAJEEL] Don't get soft on me!
Hit me with your best shot! Now!
[NEPPA] Eh?
[PANTHERLILY] No matter how
many times he pummeled me
with those iron fists,
I never gave up!
[GAJEEL yells]
Hey. Tell me something...
[GAJEEL] What?
Can you explain to
me what just happened?
My sword is made from
metal like your body,
so why did it
shatter to pieces?
Isn't it obvious?
This makes all
the difference, pal.
Well, that and what
I got on the inside...
There's iron in my soul.
My mind and body
are stronger than steel!
All your acid will
never eat that away!
[NEPPA] Sploosh!
And it'll never
break my spirit!
That's the strongest of all!
[NEPPA] Uh oh. He cut the acid?!
[COSMOS grunts]
[COSMOS] No! You blew away
all of my lovely spore bombs!
But still, I have many
beautifully deadly plants
at my disposal.
[WENDY] What now? I gotta think.
Even though I don't
understand her magic.
I can't lose.
What would
Natsu do to win?
Yeah, definitely.
That's exactly
what he would do.
[LEADER] Damn you!
I don't understand!
How can you even touch me?
Are you some kind of monster?!
[NATSU] Sorry,
I'm not a monster...
But I am a Fire Dragon Slayer.
[LEADER] No!
[NATSU] I think you're way
overdue for a beat-down!
[LEADER] Where is all this
strength coming from?!
How can he still have
so much magic power?!
[grunts]
Did you seriously think
you could take it away?
Think again!
[LEADER] How dare you.
With that, you've
truly made yourself
an enemy of the kingdom!
[NATSU] You know, I'm not
too worried about that...
You should be, though.
Because it's an even bigger
mistake to make yourself
an enemy of the
Fairy Tail guild.
[gasps]
[UOSUKE yelling]
[NATSU] And that
means everybody in it.
[NEPPA yelling]
We're not scared
of the kingdom
or anybody who tries
to bring us down!
[WENDY] Shattering Light:
Sky Drill!
[MIRAJANE] Hyaah!
[NATSU] We never
give up the fight!
[ALL groaning]
Oh!
Nice.
Oh, hi!
[HAPPY] Natsu!
[WENDY] Wow, you're all here!
[LUCY] Talk about
perfect timing!
Yeah, this is
totally awesome!
[MIRAJANE] I'll say!
And it looks like
everybody's okay!
By the skin
of our teeth...
And we're gonna be even
better once we figure a way
to get out of this dungeon.
We lost... But how?
[NATSU] Okay, scumbag!
Tell us where the exit is, or
you're gonna get executed.
He's scary.
[NATSU] Ugh. Well,
that took forever,
but I think I finally
see sweet daylight again!
[HAPPY] I was worried
we wouldn't make it
past those creeps.
[NATSU] We always do,
little buddy!
Hold on, who's that
standing by the exit?
Don't you think they
look kinda familiar?
[HAPPY] Yeah, weird...
I was just thinkin'
the exact same thing!
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time:
The Kingdom 'til Tomorrow!
[NATSU] Wait a second... Whoa.
I totally know that smell!
[HAPPY] Huh?
What in the heck
is going on here?!