[ULTEAR] At last the
games are underway.
With all their spectacle.
And of course,
Jellal couldn't be
satisfied with watching
from the sidelines.
I guess that makes our
secret meeting with that group
from Fairy Tail pretty
meaningless now,
wouldn't you say?
I'd say it was
very meaningful.
At least as far as Jellal
and Erza are concerned.
[Ultear chuckles]
♪
Ready for action?
Let's get things started
with the first contest of
the Grand Magic Games,
one that we call "Hidden"!
[CHAPATI] The first challenger
has stepped forward!
Representing Quatro
Cerberus; it's Yaeger!
[CHAPATI] From Mermaid Heel,
the adorable Beth Vanderwood!
[CHAPATI]
From Raven Tail, Nalpudding!
[CHAPATI] Blue Pegasus
sends out Eve Tilm!
Gotta love those lively cheers!
[CHAPATI] Keep your
eyes on this one, folks!
From Sabertooth, the minstrel
who sings to the red moon:
Rufus Lore!
[CHAPATI]
From Lamia Scale, Lyon Bastia!
[CHAPATI] From Fairy Tail
Team A, the icy Gray Fullbuster!
[CHAPATI] From Fairy
Tail Team B, Juvia Loxar!
The competitors
have been chosen
and the long wait
is finally over!
Grab a refreshment and
get glued to your seat,
because you're not
gonna want to miss
a single nail-biting
moment of Hidden!
[HAPPY] Night of Shooting Stars!
It's time for the
Grand Magic Games,
and I couldn't be more excited!
Allow me to go
over the rules just
one more time,
so no one gets confused!
[MAVIS] Each team is made up
of five members at the most.
But according
to what Porlyusica
said about the
situation with Wendy.
[PORLYUSICA]
No need for water-works, child.
I'm sure you'll get to
participate, once you're well.
And make no mistake,
you will recover
now that I'm here.
On my honor as a healer.
The organizers
do allow reserve
members for when
something happens.
Poor little Wendy was attacked
by those meanies in Raven Tail.
But hopefully she'll
still get a chance
to take part in the games!
[MAVIS] Eight teams
made it past the qualifying
round to move on
to the main competition.
Including two different
teams from Fairy Tail!
I'm so proud!
Those are the only teams I care
about, so I'll skip the others.
[JET AND DROY] You can
do whatever you want!
[MAVIS]
The whole tournament will
take place over the
course of five days.
Why don't we take a
closer look at the schedule?
Each day is divided
into two parts:
some sort of contest,
followed by a battle.
The teams can
choose any member
they want to participate
in the first part.
And this here will tell us how
the scores are calculated.
[MAVIS] But, for
the battles, it's the
organizers who choose
the participants!
You can score points
for wins and draws.
But a loss will earn you and
your team a big ol' goose egg.
This whole process
repeats over five days.
And whichever team has the most
points at the end
is declared the winner!
So let's wish the
Fairy Tail teams good luck!
[crowd cheers]
[MATO] Now, will each
team's participant in
the Hidden game,
kindly step forward?
See ya later.
You got this, Gray!
You better not lose, snowflake!
Ya hear me, pal?
We're better than
Gajeel's team and
those Saber jerks
and Raven, uhhh.
You gotta hide
and seek like a real man!
There are two questions
on everyone's minds.
First and foremost, just what
kind of game will "Hidden" be?
And who would you say
is the favorite in this
mysterious competition?
Hmm.
It's safe to assume
that Rufus of Sabertooth
is probably the
odds-on favorite.
But Gray from Fairy Tail is
a dark horse in the running.
Let's ask today's
special guest.
Miss Jenny Realight
from Blue Pegasus!
My fave?
I'll be rooting
for Eve, of course.
He's got this in the bag!
[cheeering crowd]
I hope you realize.
That even though our souls
are connected I don't
intend on losing to you.
Yeah, of course not.
I wanna win too.
My mind is set on winning
the competition as well.
And then fair Juvia's heart!
Creep alert.
Somebody's getting a
taste of their own medicine.
Ya know, before
we start I got
one question that
I've been dyin' to ask.
What are you?
[MATO] Who me?
My silly boy, I'm a pumpkin,
as you can plainly see.
Sorry.
Was I not supposed to
ask ya that or somethin'?
Well, he certainly looks
like a pumpkin to me.
Well duh.
Of course he looks like
a pumpkin on the outside.
But what's inside there?
He's always been
a big part of the games.
So I guess I never
really thought about it.
[BETH] Yeah I figured
he had to be
somebody on the
event staff in a costume.
[EVE AND BETH] Good job sir.
You've created
an excellent character.
[MATO] Thank you.
But I'm really only doing
this because it's so fun-kin!
Those bad puns are
gonna get old real quick.
Before we start I
got a little problem, see.
I don't know exactly what
this Hidden game is all about.
But I think something
stinks around here.
And that something
being that
there's two Fairy twerps
competing in this thing.
No other guild
is gonna get the chance
to have two members
in each round,
so I say they got
an unfair advantage.
What?
[MATO] I understand your
concern, but it can't be helped.
We never dreamed
that one guild could
have two teams make
it past the qualifier.
It really is an amazing feat.
I have no qualms with it.
In fact I remember
something that I once heard.
[RUFUS] A wise man
told me "two heads
aren't necessarily
better than one."
If I gotta beat two
fairies, bring it on!
I sure ain't gonna
raise a fuss over it.
Are you giving
us some advice?
A couple of words of wisdom
from the reigning champion?
[RUFUS] All I'm saying
is having a comrade
could prove to
be a disadvantage.
There are a myriad of ways they
could be used against you.
If they were to leak
information or be held
hostage your hand
would be easily forced.
You'd be wise
to remember that.
Yeah sure,
I'll write it down later.
[MATO] Open the field!
What the?
[LUCY] A town!
[ERZA] Amazing!
That's so cool.
This game's already crazy!
[crowd gasps]
Whoa!
They can fit an entire
city right in the
middle of the arena?
I've never seen
anything like it before.
[JELLAL] A manifestation
on such a large scale.
How much magic
energy does that require?
Juvia? Lyon?
Where in the heck
did everybody go?
All the others just disappeared.
Now I see.
So this is the game, is it?
High stakes Hide-and-Seek.
Should I be hidin'?
Or should I be
seekin' instead?
I used to play this
game when I was a little kid.
[YEAGER] Is there
somebody looking for us?
[CHAPATI] Those of you
in the stands can catch all
the exciting action in
crystal-clear lacrima-vision.
[CHAPATI]
I bet the eight contestants in
the arena wish
they had that luxury.
But that would make it too easy.
[CHAPATI] Speaking of easy,
here are the rules of the game.
All the players are hiding
and seeking at the same time!
What does that mean?
[CHAPATI] The main
objective in Hidden is to
locate the other players.
Once you've done that, you'll
have to land an attack on them!
[CHAPATI] The player
that successfully
connects
their attack,
whether or not it
does any damage,
will then be awarded one point.
Wait. Now what's
going on?
[GRAY] Aw man,
there's hundreds of 'em!
What's with all the look-alikes?
Why are you
getting all pukey?
The thought of that many Grays
just really grosses me out, man.
That's extremely difficult.
Even after knowing
Gray for all these years.
I'd probably have trouble
finding the real one.
[CHAPATI] I know they're pretty.
But those copies aren't
just for show, folks.
Attack one of your fake
competitors by mistake,
and it'll cost you one point!
It's time to disappear like a
black cat in a dark alleyway.
Fade into your surroundings
and hide in plain sight.
[CHAPATI] Let's play Hidden!
[YEAGER] This game
isn't really about
hiding as much as seeking.
It's gonna be tough
figuring out who
the real enemies
are in here, though.
Oh, there are so many beautiful
Grays to feast my eyes on!
But I don't
just have to look,
surely I can wrap my
arms around at least one!
This is heavenly.
[buzzer]
[CHAPATI] And with
that bear hug attack,
Juvia from Fairy
Tail B loses one point!
[CHAPATI] She will be put into
a ten second time-out and
then forced to start again
from another part of the arena.
The same is true if you
are attacked by another player.
One point taken off,
time-out, and then it's
starting all over again
from somewhere else!
What an idiot.
This could prove to be a little
bit of an issue for poor Juvia.
We wouldn't be
having this problem
if I were playing the game.
[CHAPATI] You are allowed
as many restarts
as you need,
but the clock is ticking.
The game will last for
thirty minutes, and of course,
whoever has the most points
at the end takes first place!
[GRAY] I can't believe this.
Finding the real people in
here is gonna be impossible.
[NALPUDDING] You dimwit.
You don't have a snowball's
chance if it takes
you this long to
figure out the game.
[GRAY] You're with Raven Tail!
[NALPUDDING]
As a matter of fact I am.
The name's Nalpudding.
Well, it's awfully
nice of you to
come find me like this.
[Nalpudding laughs]
'Cause that means
I don't have to find you!
Ice Hammer!
Oh yeah!
Is there something different
about his maker magic now?
And that's what training
will do for ya, guys.
Thanks for givin'
me my first point!
[GRAY] What the?
I clearly just pounded the guy!
[Nalpudding laughs]
No way!
[NALPUDDING] Nice try.
But this here is
the real thing, see?
I didn't know he'd
be that easy to trick.
Neither did I.
And that means another Fairy
Tail team is gonna lose a point.
Man. What a
major screw-up!
Oh well. At least I
learned something.
You can use your copies
to get close to an enemy.
And then, when they attack
and reveal themselves
you can take them by
surprise and score a point.
[GRAY]
That's how you play Hidden!
Everybody's totally
blended in with the crowds.
How are we supposed to figure
who's real and
who's not in this thing?
I'm glad I'm
not playing this one.
I get lost in a
crowd really easily.
And as we've just seen,
any careless actions
could cause you to be
revealed to the enemy.
How will you proceed.
Gray?
There are a
ton of people in here.
And most of 'em are fakes.
[NALPUDDING] Oh Gray.
You make this too easy.
Come on!
He lost another point?
This sucks. Why is he
coming after me so hard?
[NALPUDDING]
This game is getting really fun!
[CHAPATI] The tension is so
thick in this game of Hidden,
you could cut it with
a knife, with Raven Tail's
Nalpudding quickly
taking the lead.
[CHAPATI] Say, on a field
full of copies of yourself
and your enemies,
how would you figure
out who was real,
and who was just a fake?
There are
a variety of ways
to suss out
which ones are real.
One might begin
by trying to detect
an opponent's magic power.
[JENNY] I'm sure our
crafty little Eve will
figure out a more
sophisticated method.
Searching for
magic might be a start.
It would certainly get
you in the general vicinity.
But pinpointing a
foe would be tough.
Keep screwin' up and it's
gonna cost us the game, Gray!
That little purple guy got
ya two times in a row!
What's up
with Raven Tail?
You know staring
isn't very nice, Blondie.
They're the ones
that attacked Wendy,
and for some
strange reason it seems
like they're only targeting
Gray in this round.
Maybe I'll teach
you some manners.
[IVAN (ALEXAI)]
That's enough, Flare.
Ivan, you scum.
I know you can win this, Gray!
Square one again.
[BETH] Carrot Missiles!
Aw shoot!
I totally missed that guy.
[GRAY] What is that?
Ah yeah!
I was sick of waitin' for
the chance to use magic!
[LYON] So was I!
You.
I've found my rival.
Finally.
[JUVIA] You can't hide
from me, my darling!
Holy crap!
What a view!
[GRAY] Look, I don't need
any help from you, got it?
I'm aware of that.
That was so worth it.
As a matter of fact,
I'm determined to beat you.
Because of the
promise master made.
I'll bet that promise
has something to do with me.
Yes.
[GAJEEL] Are you kidding me?
I don't want anything to do with
that big, stupid freak show!
Well I don't
have any objection.
But getting put on the B team
is kind of insulting, though.
Then what if I
sweeten the deal?
Yes.
The members of the winning
team get to do whatever
they want to the losing
team for one entire day.
That sounds to
me like it's more of a
punishment game for
the ones on the bottom.
[LAXUS] Whatever we want, huh?
Hey... get me some food.
{NATSU] Right away, Mr. Laxus!
[GAJEEL] One whole day?
Shake it, baby!
[LUCY] With pleasure!
That could be pretty sweet.
Bring me some
salt-grilled mackerel, please!
[ERZA] Of course, ma'am.
Anything that we want?
Oh my.
If master says'
that I have to do this.
Then I've got no choice.
That's true.
Is this some kinda joke?
Hey, Gramps, if you're gonna
make crazy rules like that.
Then they have gotta be fair!
That means they better work
if our team wins this thing too!
Yes.
Of course they will.
Yeah.
I know exactly
what I want.
[NATSU] Gimme
a Happy impression!
[LAXUS AND GAJEEL]
Aye!
Hold on. That's all
you'd want from them?
I want my wish.
So I'm not planning on losing.
Bring it on!
[NALPUDDING] Two fairies
for the price of one!
Why is he only
going after our guild?
I don't know.
What in the hell
is this guy's problem?
[CHAPATI]
Wow, would ya look at this?
Our city is turning into
a winter wonderland!
That's gotta be Eve.
[EVE] It's a shame
there are some wizards
here that aren't
affected by the cold.
But most of them are.
I see.
When people are
cold they start to shiver.
And you can see
steam from their breath.
But it doesn't work
that way for the copies.
Pretty smart strategy,
I can see you!
Right there!
[CHAPATI] Eve accumulates
a flurry of points!
And the ice wizard Lyon answers
with a storm of his creation!
Unfortunately for you I've spent
my life training in the cold!
Yeah, I kinda figured.
Again?
What's the deal?
Why is this freak
so obsessed with me?
We're still yet to
see any movement on the
board by the top-seeded Rufus
of the Sabertooth guild.
He's hasn't lost any points,
but he hasn't scored any either.
[RUFUS] I find this
game dreadfully boring.
Wait!
There he is!
[RUFUS] I've committed
this song to memory.
The rhythm of their
heartbeats, their footsteps,
the tone of their magic.
That's a pretty conspicuous
hiding place if ya ask me!
Ya think that guy
actually wants
the others to find
him for some reason?
Gray, right above you!
It's all there.
Inside my mind.
[RUFUS] Memory Make.
What is this magic?
I've never heard of it.
[RUFUS]
Night of Shooting Stars!
You could really learn
a thing or two about hiding!
Oh, no! A fake?
[RUFUS] Not quite!
You haven't lost a point.
That was a memory
of my being there.
[Nalpudding cries out]
[RUFUS]
I find that's much more
effective than
using mere decoys.
[CHAPATI] And the hits
rain down from above,
turning the scoreboard
upside down!
This is what you'd expect
from a guy like Rufus!
Sabertooth takes the lead!
[RUFUS] The organizers
really need to work harder.
These games aren't
the least bit interesting.
[RUFUS] After all.
I was still able
to claim victory
without even needing to hide.
They may have
spotted me but
nobody even came
close to touching me.
[RUFUS] The best they could do
was merely chase my memory.
Wow.
That was unbelievable.
No kidding.
I think I'm starting
to see why
they're the number
one guild in Fiore.
Man.
Thattaboy Rufus!
I can't wait until everybody
sees what Sting can do!
Yay for Rufus!
That's some kind
of maker magic?
He's truly a force
to be reckoned with.
I'll watch out.
But we can still beat them.
[GRAY] Ya think
you've outsmarted us?
This game's called Hidden,
so start playin' by the rules!
[GRAY] Aw crap!
That Rufus guy was standing
completely open up there.
But still Nalpudding passed
him over to attack Gray.
[crowds cheering]
[CHAPATI] And with that,
the game is over!
[CHAPATI] So let's take a
look at the ol' scoreboard!
That was absolutely
pitiful, Lyon!
You should be ashamed!
Please master, you
should really calm down!
Eve could've done a
whole lot worse I guess.
Not too bad.
Fifth place, huh?
We'd better step up our game.
We gotta give Beth
some credit for trying!
[CHAPATI] Just as we expected,
Sabertooth claims the top spot!
[YAJIMA] Stupendously done!
[CHAPATI] Both Fairy Tail
teams gave it their all.
But unfortunately,
it wasn't enough
to get them out of last place.
[YAJIMA] Better luck next time!
Well what do you expect
from the weakest guild in Fiore?
They're such losers!
Get used to being
in dead last, ya has-beens!
You'd better stop laughing
at us right now, or else!
Ooh!
He's mad!
What, are you gonna cry?
Natsu.
Let 'em laugh, they won't
be doing it for very long.
[GRAY] Sorry.
[LUCY] Don't worry about it.
It's only the first game.
[GRAY] Raven Tail.
And that pompous wizard.
I will be gettin
payback for this,
so they should watch out.
Coming up next is the
battle part of the contest!
One member of each team
will participate in a match.
But this isn't
a tournament setup!
It's the game's organizers
who decide who's
going to be duking
it out in the battles, right?
I'm sure they'll set up some
spectacular displays
of magical skills.
I've just received the lineups,
so we'll find out how
spectacular those will be!
[CHAPATI] Our very first match
of this year's Grand Magic Games
will test the abilities
of Fairy Tail A's,
zodiac wielder, Lucy Heartfilia.
Okay!
[CHAPATI]
Against the "Crimson Intensity.
Raven Tail's Flare Corona!
Too bad for you, blondie!
♪
[HAPPY]
You've totally got this, Lucy!
Oh man, I hope so,
cause that Flare girl
seems super crazy to me.
[NATSU] Do you hear that?
I think she's
mumbling something.
[HAPPY] "Blondie."
[NATSU] Huh?
[HAPPY] She's saying, "Blondie."
[NATSU] Bloody?
[HAPPY] No!
Blondie!
[NATSU] Bra D? She's
talking about a D-Cup bra?
[HAPPY] Get your
mind outta the gutter!
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next Time: Lucy vs. Flare!
[HAPPY] Who knows,
maybe she is saying,
"Bra D" for some reason."
[NATSU] "Bra D!"
[HAPPY] At the least.