[MATO]
Let the Grand Magic Games'
preliminary round,
Sky Labyrinth begin!
[GRAY] Well, if it's a race
then we better get moving.
[NATSU] Let's go!
No, wait!
[NATSU] What's the problem?
[ERZA] The rules state
that all five members
must reach the goal.
So we can't leave without Wendy.
[LUCY] You're right!
Wendy!
Crap! What're we
gonna do now?
[ELFMAN] Why wait
for a little girl,
when you've got a
man who's ready to go?
♪
We've got a roster change!
He's so much stronger now!
What're you doing, bro?
[GRAY] He's doin' what
needs to be done!
We don't have time to wait
around for Wendy to show up!
[NATSU] Elfman to the rescue!
You guys just
leave it to me!
[ERZA] Lisanna!
Happy!
[HAPPY] Aye?
[LISANNA] Yeah?
What is it?
[ERZA] I need you two to go
look for Wendy and Carla!
I'm really worried
that they might've run
into some kind of trouble.
Okay!
We'll go ask around town and
see what we can find out!
Aye, sir!
Good luck to ya!
[HAPPY]
Go team!
[ELFMAN] Manly!
[GRAY] We're getting
close to the entrance!
[NATSU] Our first step to
bein' number one in Fiore!
We're takin' that title!
Right, Team Fairy Tail?
[ALL] Oh yeah!
[HAPPY] Sky Labyrinth!
[NARRATOR] Here's a quick
reminder of the rules of the
preliminary round
to refresh your memory.
[NARRATOR] There are one
hundred and thirteen teams
participating in this
year's Grand Magic Games.
[NARRATOR] The purpose
of the preliminary round is to
narrow down the number
of participating teams.
Only eight will be allowed to
move on to the main competition.
[NARRATOR]
Each team must head into the
Sky Labyrinth from
their respective inn.
From there,
they have to find their way
to the tournament's
coliseum, Domus Flau.
The first eight teams
to reach the goal
qualify to participate
in the main events.
Additionally, participants
are free to use magic
however they see
fit within the labyrinth.
There are no
restrictions whatsoever.
[MATO] Remember.
The Grand Magic Games' planning
committee is not responsible
for any loss of life that may
occur within the Sky Labyrinth!
Good luck, everyone!
[GRAY] Whoa, it's some kinda
crazy, three-dimensional maze.
[NATSU] I really
suck at stuff like this!
[LUCY] Don't give up already!
We have to finish
in the top eight.
Otherwise,
we can kiss the title
of "number one in
Fiore" goodbye.
Yeah, you're right!
We gotta get through
this if we wanna get
the chance to kick
Sabertooth's butt!
Let's make sure we reach
the goal before they do.
Real men never settle for
anything less than first place!
When we were on the ground
the coliseum was to the east.
I think we should
head in that direction.
[LUCY] I've got just
the thing to help us out!
Open!
Gate of the Compass!
[LUCY] Pyxis!
[Pyxis emits gibberish]
We need your help, Pyxis!
Can you please show
us which way is east?
East is thataway!
Yes, I'm well aware.
Because I brought
along a regular compass.
[LUCY] Thanks for
the help anyway, Pyxis.
[Pyxis emits gibberish]
[NATSU] Alright, east!
Here we come!
[ELFMAN] A real man charges
straight towards the goal!
[LUCY] Not to be a downer.
But with the way
this place is laid out.
I don't think we're gonna
be able to go straight east.
[GRAY] We're gonna have
a hard enough time just
tryin' to figure
out which way is up!
Natsu. You're
not feeling sick?
Nuh-uh, you'd think
I'd be pukin' my guts out
but I feel just fine.
[MATO] Allow me to explain!
A special magic was cast on
the Sky Labyrinth allowing
participants with weaknesses
such as motion sickness and
fear of heights to be
able to compete on
equal terms in the
preliminary round!
[ERZA] I see.
[NATSU] Guess it's
like Troia magic.
I seriously doubt
the other wizards
get motion sickness
as easily as Natsu.
I know what ya mean.
He's kind of a baby.
Hey I can
hear ya, y'know!
[ERZA] Let's keep
heading eastward!
[ALL] Right!
[GRAY] What the--?
[ELFMAN] Whoa, I'm gettin'
dizzy just lookin' at it!
[LUCY] Yeah, I feel like
I'm gonna fall right in.
[ERZA] We're wasting time!
Let's go!
Real men don't hesitate;
they always keep
their eye on the prize!
[LUCY] Okay, I get it!
But how long is
this creepy tunnel?
Does it really matter?
Our goal's at the end of it!
[ELFMAN] Don't worry, I got ya!
Thanks man!
That was a close one!
You're lucky that
I caught ya in time.
We could have lost you.
When he was
talking about possible
"loss of life"
he wasn't bluffing.
[GRAY] Watch your step, cause
I don't think anybody would
survive fallin' headfirst
into the city from this thing.
[ELFMAN We gotta be
more careful about choosin'
our path from now on.
Guys, we're never
gonna reach the goal
if we keep lookin' down!
C'mon, we need to
keep headin' eastward!
[ERZA] I think it would
be prudent for us to
take notes as we move along.
[LUCY] On what?
We should write
down the path we've
taken from our
starting point.
And the locations we've passed.
We need to know
precisely where we
are in order to make progress.
That sure would help us
stop running around in circles.
No joke.
Guess we better
start mappin' stuff out.
Come on.
That ain't gonna work here.
How're we supposed
to make a
map of this
topsy-turvy place?
[GRAY] Quit whinin' and help.
Can't you sniff out
the goal or somethin'?
[NATSU] Doncha think
I woulda done that by now?
[LUCY] The magic they
cast on the labyrinth
must've dulled
your sense of smell.
[ERZA] The conditions are
the same for every team.
Let's keep moving!
[cheers]
What do you
mean Wendy's gone?
[NAB] Hang on.
Are you saying she's missing?
[HAPPY] We can't
find her or Carla!
Don't the rules say each
team's gotta have five members?
Don't tell me they've
been disqualified.
No, luckily
my brother stepped
in as a last-minute replacement.
Elfman's in the
preliminary round too?
That's not fair!
If I'd been there they
would've chosen me to
join the team not
that big dummy!
Uh, yeah sure.
Happy and I are gonna
start looking for them.
I need you two
to go and tell the others.
We'll have a better chance
of finding them if we
split into teams and use
Warren's telepathy.
[HAPPY] This city is
huge so we've got a
lot of ground to cover.
[ROMEO] Got it.
I'm worried.
I hope they haven't
run into any sorta trouble.
[NAB] Yeah, me too
but try not to dwell on it.
Let's hurry and get back to the
others so we can fill them in.
[ROMEO] Right.
[ERZA] East is that direction.
[LUCY] This maze is harder to
map out than I thought it'd be.
Well, whaddya expect
when everything
around you looks the same?
Hey, Erza.
[ERZA] Yes.
I heard it, too.
You're the one who told us
to go this way, ya little runt!
[KOZARU]
Don't try to blame this on me!
[NOPPO]
I don't care whose fault it is!
All I know is we've
been here before.
[REGENT] That's what I'm sayin'!
We're goin' around in circles!
[KOZARU] Just shut up
and keep moving!
We're runnin' out of time!
I almost forgot.
It's been so quiet
that it's easy to
forget there are
other guilds in here.
Man, you gotta be kiddin' me.
You again.
It's the Fairy Tail guild!
[REGENT] This some kinda joke?
[NATSU] Aw, not those clowns!
[NARRATOR] As you may
recall, this is Twilight Ogre.
The guild that harassed
Fairy Tail while Natsu
and the others were
stuck on Tenrou Island.
But all that changed
when our heroes returned.
[NARRATOR] Fairy Tail turned
the tables on Twilight Ogre
and gave them the
punishment they deserved.
Well, I see your guild
is just as shoddy as ever.
[KOZARU] You're lame!
[GRAY] I'm surprised to see
you losers in the tournament.
[TEEBO] You got no
right to call us losers.
You're the guild that
always comes in last place!
Fairy Tail's takin'
first place this year!
Just you watch!
We'll see about that.
[LUCY] Whoa, hold on a sec!
You wanna fight us right here?
[NOPPO] Why not?
We can use magic
without restrictions!
I don't blame
ya for bein' scared!
[TEEBO] You Fairy Tail
punks are goin' down!
These guys'll never learn.
I'm fired up now!
We're really going
through with this?
The fewer the rivals,
the better our chances.
Yeah, you've got
a good point, Erza.
You're gonna pay for makin' us
look bad in front of the boss!
[REGENT] Let's pulverize 'em!
You're gonna be cryin' for
mercy when we get done with ya!
We don't have time
to mess with you.
'Cause we gotta
take down Sabertooth.
To be number one in Fiore!
[TEEBO] No way!
[rival guild cry out]
[ERZA] What now?
[NATSU]
Aw man, I don't like this!
[LUCY]
What the heck's goin' on?
[GRAY] The ground's moving!
Well no, technically.
It seems the labyrinth
itself has started to rotate!
[ALL] Seriously?
[ERZA] It seems the labyrinth
itself has started to rotate!
[NATSU] No way!
For real?
[NATSU] Nobody
warned us about this!
[Natsu and Lucy cry out]
Whoa, what's
happening to it?
I dunno but
it can't be good!
[HAPPY] Uh-oh!
Lisanna, look!
[LISANNA]
They're dropping like flies!
Oh no. If they fall
they'll be disqualified!
Really?
I hope they're gonna
be all right up there.
[ERZA]
It's turning on its Z-axis!
[GRAY] Hear that?
We've gotta move
to its sides, you guys!
[LUCY] Uh, we would
but we're already falling!
[NATSU] If only Happy were here!
[ELFMAN] Who needs
a flyin' cat...?
When you've got a
man like me on your team.
[NATSU] Whoa.
Nice catch.
Thanks Elfman,
you're the best!
Nah, just lookin'
out for my pals.
[GRAY] Are you okay over there?
[ALL] We're good!
It's stopped moving.
I dunno who came
up with this contraption,
but they're pretty
messed up in the head.
[ERZA] I'm not surprised by
the intricacy of the labyrinth.
It's designed to narrow over one
hundred teams down to eight.
[GRAY] It looks like that
last move was enough
to get rid of a lot of 'em.
[crowd babbling]
[LUCY] What's that?
Did those jerks make a map, too?
It appears they have.
Talk about a lucky break!
If we combine our notes
with Twilight Ogre's then
we'll have an even
better map of this place!
[TEEBO] Hey! What do
you think you're doin'?
[ERZA]
Oh, does this belong to you?
Yeah!
Now give it back!
[ERZA] Not gonna happen.
[TEEBO] You're not
gonna get away with this!
[MATO]
Another one bites the dust.
How about that.
I just figured out how we're
going to get ahead
in the preliminaries.
Whoa, what's with the
creepy look in your eyes?
[distant voices]
[MATO] The preliminary
round is about to
take a very serious turn.
[MATO] A vast majority
of the teams will
soon be eliminated,
one right after the other!
This is so exciting
I can barely contain myself!
[NATSU] May not be nice but
you know what we gotta do!
We've gotta start stealin
everyone else's maps!
You think this is
a race but it's a battle!
Cause we're fightin' a manly
map war like none other!
[NATSU] We're experts
when it comes
to kickin' the butts
of our rivals!
[ERZA] I'll take this.
Oh you can take
whatever you want!
[NATSU] Way to go,
team! We got six maps!
I don't wanna sound
stupid, but I got no idea how
I'm supposed to
read this damn thing.
[GRAY] This kinda
stuff is Lucy's specialty.
Let's ask her.
Yeah! Sweet!
All we gotta do is
gather as many maps
as we can and then
let her figure 'em out.
[LUCY] Who, me?
Good luck.
[LUCY] Thanks.
Hand 'em over, chumps!
Give us all of your maps!
I've already got
three of 'em so far!
Not too shabby,
but I've got seven!
I'm so sorry.
No, you're not.
[GRAY] It's gonna move again!
[ELFMAN] Hurry and
grab on to somethin'!
[ELFMAN] It stopped!
[NATSU] Awesome!
Alright team, let's
get back to business!
[ALZACK] What's up, Max?
Y'have any luck?
[MAX] I'm afraid not.
You'd think a little girl and
her talking cat would be
conspicuous,
but no one's seen 'em.
[WARREN] Yeah It's weird.
It's not like Wendy and Carla
to just wander off like that.
[MAX] We need to
hurry and find them
'cause I'm sure
the team's concerned.
It's gotta be hard for
them to focus on the race.
Hey did you find
anything, Warren?
[WARREN]
Nope, not even a single lead.
We've scoured
every inch of Crocus
but haven't seen
hide nor hair of them.
I suppose we could
check Domus Flau
but I doubt we'll
find them there.
[WARREN] The only place
left is the royal palace!
[HAPPY] That reminds me!
[LISANNA] What is it?
Earlier today, Carla
mentioned something about
going on a sightseeing
tour of the city with Wendy.
Well, in that case...
Maybe they are at the palace.
[HAPPY] There's only
one way to find out!
[LISANNA] Let's go!
[LUCY] I feel like there's
no point in trying to head east
from the surface
of the labyrinth.
We're just gonna
end up running around in
circles because the
stupid thing keeps rotating.
Is that why you
decided to bring
us to the center of it instead?
Yeah, I thought
it was gonna be easier to
find east from here
but apparently I was wrong.
[ERZA] Who would've thought
we'd find such a peaceful
landscape in the center
of this monstrosity?
[GRAY] It'd be more peaceful
if it wasn't upside down.
[ERZA] As if that
wasn't strange enough.
It would appear there's
no east or west anymore.
[GRAY] Geez, even
our compass is dizzy.
[ELFMAN] Man, this sucks!
There's no tellin' which
way we're supposed to go!
[ERZA] True but we can't
afford to stop moving either.
[LUCY] Yes! I've been
waiting for this moment!
What's gotten into you?
I bet this crazy place's got
her brain all scrambled.
[LUCY]
Nope, my brain's just fine!
Open, Gate of the Compass!
Pyxis!
Not that weird
duck thing again.
[NATSU]
Why does it look so scared?
Erza's compass must've
traumatized him.
[ERZA] I didn't
mean to upset him.
Okay pal!
Don't be scared--this
is your time to shine!
Her compass is
completely useless!
Observe.
It keeps spinning.
[LUCY] See?
I told ya!
We could really use
your help right now.
[ERZA]
I apologize for upsetting you.
Would you please assist us?
That's one
simpleminded Spirit.
Yeah, but I bet he's
still smarter than Erza.
[ERZA] What did you say?
[NATSU AND GRAY] Nothin'!
Nothin' at all!
[LUCY] East is that way!
[GRAY] One small problem,
"that way" is "up"!
[NATSU] You sure
he's right about this?
[LUCY] I'm positive!
Trust me, Celestial Spirits
are way stronger
than regular old compasses!
[ELFMAN] Any ideas on how
we're gonna get up there?
[ERZA] Isn't it obvious?
Give it a sec.
[ALL] We fall?
That's so not cool!
[ELFMAN] Would ya
look at those birds.
[GRAY] This sure
is peaceful, ain't it?
[LUCY] C'mon, we've worked
too hard and fallen too far
to get knocked out
of the preliminary round.
We've gotta get back at it.
This is no time
to be relaxing.
We're still in the
middle of a race.
[ERZA] Let's go!
We're taking first place
in the preliminary round!
[ALL] Oh yeah!
[ELFMAN] How in the
heck were they able
to squeeze an ocean
into this thing?
[LUCY] Who cares about that,
how long is this freakin' path?
[GRAY] Quit whinin' and look up!
[ERZA] The sky
above us isn't real.
It's been painted on.
[NATSU] She's right!
Check it out!
If that's the case, then this
must actually lead somewhere!
[ELFMAN]
And that's gotta be the goal!
[NATSU] Okay.
Team!
It's time for one final sprint!
[ALL] Let's go!
[LISANNA] So this is
the king of Fiore's castle.
[HAPPY] The luminaria
palace, Mercurius.
[LISANNA] This is the
first time I've ever seen it!
[HAPPY] Yeah, me too.
Stop right there!
Where do you
think you're going?
The grounds are closed.
[LISANNA] Sorry,
we're just looking for our
guild members
who've gone missing.
One of them was
supposed to participate
in the Grand Magic
Games preliminary round.
[HAPPY] We've searched
all over Crocus,
so this is the only place
left for us to check!
Hey. Let's just
let 'em in.
What?
Well, I guess there's no harm.
His Majesty is looking
forward to the games
so we certainly don't want
anything to interfere with that.
But don't go any farther
than the castle courtyard.
[HAPPY] We won't!
Thanks, guys!
Are you kiddin' me?
I can't believe it was so easy!
So what's the story man?
[WARREN]
The guards let Happy and
Lisanna inside the palace gates!
[MAX] How come those
jerks never let me in?
I'm kinda surprised
they let us do this.
Well, the gardens
have been open to
tourists in the past,
just not this late at night.
[HAPPY] I think we
should split up and search.
[LISANNA] Good idea!
We'll use Warren's telepathy
to keep in touch, okay?
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
Got it!
We're on our way
to Mercurius right now!
[ALZACK] I really hope
that those two are okay!
[MAX] The games
haven't even started yet
and there's already trouble?
We're really gettin'
off on the wrong foot!
[MATO] Elfman Strauss.
[MATO] Erza Scarlet.
[MATO] Gray Fullbuster.
[MATO] Lucy Heartfilia.
[MATO] And Natsu Dragneel.
[MATO] Congratulations
Team Fairy Tail!
You've cleared
the preliminary round!
[NATSU] We did it!
Why do you sound
so surprised?
I knew we were gonna make it.
I'm dying to know, did
we come in first place?
[MATO]
Uh. No.
More like eighth place.
[MATO]
You just barely qualified.
[ALL] Eighth place?
[MATO] Attention everyone!
The eight teams
have been determined!
[MATO] The Grand Magic
Games' preliminary round,
Sky Labyrinth, is over!
[MAX]
Did Fairy Tail make the cut?
[WARREN] Yeah, which guilds
are moving on to the tournament?
[MATO] Oh, so you
wanna know who's
participating in
the main events?
Well, you'll just have
to wait until the
opening ceremonies to find out!
[ALZACK] Aw c'mon!
Why won't you just
tell us, ya killjoy?
Sounds like the
preliminary round's over.
I wonder if our
team made it through.
[LISANNA] Happy!
Is there something wrong?
[HAPPY] Look.
I found this.
[LISANNA] That purse!
I've seen it before.
Yeah, I have too.
That's Wendy's.
Now I'm worried!
What happened to them?
Just stay calm.
They're probably
not too far from here.
[HAPPY] You're right.
[LISANNA] Let's go!
[HAPPY] Aye!
Wait, you found 'em?
So they were at the palace.
Are they all right?
I think so.
It's hard to tell;
they're unconscious!
Would you please send
help as fast as possible?
Wake up, Carla!
It's me, Happy; you know,
the one you call "tomcat"?
She doesn't
seem to be injured.
That's good.
But I barely sense
any magic power from her.
Yeah, same with Carla!
Isn't there anything we can do?
She's awake!
Maybe she'll be able
to tell us what happened!
No!
Don't hurt me!
[LISANNA] It's okay.
You're safe.
It's Lisanna;
do you recognize me?
[HAPPY] I'm here with ya, too!
[WENDY] Happy.
Lisanna.
What in the world happened?
[HAPPY] We were gonna
ask you the same thing.
You don't remember?
[WENDY] No.
[NARRATOR] With Elfman filling
in for Wendy, Team Fairy Tail
managed to pass the preliminary
round to become one of the
eight teams that will compete in
the tournament's main events.
At last the stage is set for
the Grand Magic Games to begin!
[NARRATOR] Team Fairy Tail is
determined to defeat Sabertooth
and become the
number one guild in Fiore.
Can they rise from the
ashes and come out on top?
♪
[HAPPY] You did it!
But I can't believe
you came in last.
[NATSU] It must
be some kinda mistake!
[HAPPY] Nope, last place.
[NATSU] Shut up!
All that matters is
we cleared the prelims!
Now I just have
to defeat everyone
from first to seventh place!
[HAPPY] I don't follow ya.
There are eight teams and each
one has five members, right?
Then that means I gotta beat,
let's see, forty people?
[NATSU AND HAPPY]
Next time: New Guild!
[HAPPY] I gotta admit, I'm
impressed you got the math right
but that means you'd
have to fight yourself.
[NATSU]
Thirty-nine people, then!
[HAPPY] But that
includes your teammates!
Whatever.