[GAJEEL] So, you're here
for the clock piece too, huh?
I am... It's a
pleasure to meet you.
My name is Samuel. The
brains of the Legion Platoon.
An Exceed. The one Natsu
and the others mentioned.
Indeed. You actually
have something
between your ears,
young lady. I'm impressed.
[growls]
♪
[HAPPY] So this
is the clock piece?
[LUCY] It's way bigger
than I expected it to be!
I need to find a way to
snatch it from them, quick!
Looey!
You still wanna
fight, jerk?
No, I'll admit you beat
me fair and square.
Victory is yours.
I surrender.
Then will
you tell us
what the Legion
Platoon's goal is?!
Why are you trying to
collect the clock pieces?
Yeah, spill it! Also,
who are you exactly?
And why are you chasing
after a girl like Lucy?
I don't think I like
your tone, cat.
So you want
to know my tale?!
Very well! I shall
recount it to you in full,
and unadulterated detail!
Just to ensure you
get the full effect,
I'll be starting from
the very beginning.
Get ready for 'my
life in pictures!'
[LUCY] That's
really not necessary.
[HAPPY] Defying Calculation!
[DAN] I, Dan Straight,
was born in the glorious
seaport city of Seder.
Ah, good ol' Seder...
Home to an ancient brotherhood
of knights who protected
the town and its
church for generations.
My own family came from
a long line of these knights.
As a successor to this
proud family line, I lived
a happy, pampered childhood
filled with camaraderie,
and the finest of juices.
Unfortunately,
those peaceful times
were not fated
to last forever...
One day, without warning,
a civil war erupted and
split the city in two!
Wow, I never woulda
thought that you
had such a messed up past.
And your poor family
was dragged into
the fighting and had
to struggle to survive.
No... The fighting
ended in half a day,
so we made it out
relatively unscathed.
And everyone started
getting along again
pretty quickly, too!
That was quick!
We've had more
intense scuffles
at the guild hall
before lunch.
Hang on to your skirt;
the story's just beginning!
A few years later,
I fell head over heels
for my first love...
A beautiful, young maiden
who went to school with me.
I was forced to go to war
and when I came back,
I searched high and low, but
I couldn't find her anywhere!
So this girl
went missing?
Don't tell me she got caught up
in the fighting somehow!
She must've lost
her life in battle
how heartbreakingly tragic!
Her beauty was
unlike any other.
Actually, Loopyloo
looks kinda like her.
It's so sad I
can't stand it!
That's why you fell
for Lucy as soon as
you laid eyes on her!
I feel kinda bad...
but I didn't think he was gonna
share everything with us.
So, what? Did you find
her body somewhere?
Actually... I found
her completely unharmed!
[ALL] Are you kidding me?!
Great, right...?
Unfortunately, our union
didn't end up quite like
I had hoped it would.
My daily marriage
proposals brought her
so much happiness,
they frightened her!
In the end, her fear
got the best of her,
and she decided she wasn't
worthy of my affection.
And, though it took time,
I realized she was right.
I can't help but
notice that the pictures
and his story don't
really seem to match up.
Yeah, it's obvious
she couldn't stand the guy.
[DAN] Ultimately,
she rejected my proposal
and I cried my eyes out for
three full days and nights.
I decided to set out
on a sentimental journey
to soothe my
sorrow-ridden heart.
During my travels,
I crossed paths with many
a lovely maiden;
each with her own charm.
[HAPPY] He sounds like a
catcallin' slime ball to me.
So the point of your
journey wasn't to find a girl
who reminded you
of your first love?
Nah I'll never find
true love if I limit myself!
The world's a buffet...
And every gal is a dish
I'm dyin' to try!
This guy is really
starting to piss me off.
[DAN] Due to unavoidable
circumstances, no fault
of my own of course,
I was forced to part ways
with each girl I met.
[DAN] Because I devoted
my life to the knighthood
I will never know what it's
like to have love and peace.
Yeah, the story and
pictures still don't match up.
I think it's obvious
they all dumped him and ran.
It kind of makes you wonder
if someone other than
the storyteller drew
all of the pictures.
Hughes and Sugarboy
did them for me.
They used entries from my travel
journal and some old photos
I had as a reference.
Naturally there
was guesswork involved,
which means some parts might
not be entirely accurate.
I'm pretty sure the
pictures are more accurate
than your story, bub.
[DAN] Eventually, I joined
the Legion Platoon.
Since then, I've dedicated
my life to gathering
the clock pieces at
Lord Byro's behest!
That's it!
That's how the great Dan
Straight came to grace you
with his presence!
And he lived
happily ever after!
That's great... But we
really just wanted the story
on the Legion Platoon and
why you're set on gathering
the clock pieces!
Sorry Looeypie but I can't
tell you any of our secrets.
Because, if I did, Lord
Byro would dish out
some fierce punishment.
Then what was the point
of that stupid story, jerk?!
Yeah, it made no sense,
and the production value sucked.
It's obvious! I told you
my tale so that LooLoo
could learn more about
her future husband!
Now whaddya
say we tie the knot
so we can start
our honeymoon?!
[DAN] Loopyloo!
I've got a headache.
I dunno if I can put up
with any more of this.
What should
we do, Natsu?
We won't get anywhere if we keep
messin' around with this wacko.
Unfortunately we
can't just pick up
and leave
this place either.
We're supposed to wait
for the others to find
their clock pieces
and meet us here.
[NATSU groans]
I guess we'll just have
to relax here for a bit.
[LUCY] Don't "relax"!
Get over here and help me!
Hold on...
One of the members of
the Legion Platoon
seems to have vanished.
It's Coco! I just
hope she hasn't gone
and hurt herself again.
Bet you two fish she
turned tail and ran.
Why worry about her
in the first place?
She is our enemy.
That might be the case,
but she's still a little girl,
and I think there's
some good left in her.
I can be a good boy!
Don't come
any closer!
I'd really like to
avoid hurting her
if it's at all
possible...
What are you
saying, Coco?!
Don't forget, you're a
member of the Legion Platoon
and accomplishing your
mission always comes first!
Well Sammy, if you want
that clock piece, come get it.
I dare ya!
Please do refrain
from abbreviating my name.
Samuel will do
just fine, thank you.
Don't worry,
I can take him down.
You guys focus on digging
up that clock piece as fast
as you can.
You're Pantherlily,
correct?
I'm honored to meet
a senior Exceed.
Y'know when
you think about it,
that essentially makes you
like an older brother to me.
You are not worthy of
calling yourself my brother!
Now, now, don't be
so coldhearted!
I mean, we're both Exceeds.
We should at least try
to be friendly...
"Brother".
You'll have to
do better than
that to vex
me, "Sammy".
Come on. Let's go
dig up the clock piece
while Lily
keeps him busy.
Alright, fine...
Don't blame me if you lose!
I know all
about you, Lily.
Despite being an Exceed,
you sided with the humans.
How did our brethren
take that, I wonder?
What I did was
based on my convictions!
And I have never
once regretted my decision.
I can tell that you've
got quite a temper.
You'd gain much from
being craftier, like me.
Logic trumps brute force.
Sorry, pal, but
I've never been
the type to think in terms
of gains and losses.
I see. A shame
we don't have much
in common, "Brother".
[PANTHERLILY] Stop yammering
and fight me "Sammy"!
I'm happy to oblige.
En garde!
I'm much more than just
a bookworm with wings.
Allow me to demonstrate!
[digging]
[explosion]
Where in the
heck are we?!
[DROY] Those are some
weird lookin' statues!
Don't run away!
Come face me like
a true warrior!
Charging into a sword
head-on is a practice best left
to imbeciles and cannon fodder.
An intelligent fighter
considers strategy,
methodology, and outcomes
before they attack!
[SAMUEL] You have
no chance of winning...
The Legion Platoon has endured
training far more intense
than you can imagine.
Therefore, we can cope
with any situation!
My victory's assured!
[PANTHERLILY] Dammit!
Precisely as I calculated!
I even impress myself!
Now according to
my calculations,
he should've
landed around here.
[PANTHERLILY]
Behind ya, Sammy!
You're remarkably
stubborn. Aren't you?
I'm not gonna
fall for the same trick
twice in a row!
And I know Gajeel is gonna
find that clock piece
any moment now. Your victory
is far from assured!
[SAMUEL] Such confidence...
Are you not aware the ruins
are filled with traps?
You can't
be serious!
[JET] Nothin' up here!
[DROY] I don't see anything that
looks like a clock piece...
Hmmm...
There's something
scribbled on this one.
[LEVY] Lemme see... It says
"I'm hungry". Weird, huh?
[JET] Hey!
From way up here...
it kinda looks
like a clock face.
Wait, does that
mean... it should point
at "snack time" or somethin'?
Sounds good
to me!
[GAJEEL chuckles]
So all we gotta
do is move it, huh?
[SAMUEL] I told you,
there's more to me than
just intelligence. My combat
skills are unparalleled.
Statistically, you've got
no chance of winning!
[PANTHERLILY]
Gajeel... Please be careful!
[rumbling]
[crash]
Looks like
we found it!
[DROY] It's an
actual clock face.
Was there a
reason for that?
It smelled like iron; I
just wanted to make sure.
Well, now that you know,
you can carry it.
[LEVY] There's some writing...
I bet I can read it.
We don't got time to study
the thing, sweetheart.
[LEVY] No, wait!
Don't take it off!
[explosion]
I tried to tell you!
It says, "Warning!
He who takes this shall face the
wrath of the rock guardian!"
[piercing noise]
I told you not
to take it, but no,
you just had to go
and do it anyway!
Next time
talk faster!
listen to me!
[DROY and JET] Could you
save the arguing for later?!
[SAMUEL] It appears
that your comrades
have managed to
spring the trap.
Precisely
as I calculated!
I see... So that's
the reason
you drew me away from
them. You planned this!
You're powerful
and you can fly.
That made you
a prime target.
Taking all threats
out of the picture
is essential
for victory.
[piercing noise]
I think whatever's
emitting that red light
is the control
mechanism!
Yeah, and I bet
that's its weak spot!
All right, ugly!
Team Shadowgear's about
to chew you up
and spit you out!
[LEVY] I'll immobilize it first!
Solid Script Magic!
Oil!
Now it's my turn
to bring the pain!
Chain plant... Grow!
Time for me to finish it
off! High Speed!
See that? Does Shadow
Gear rule, or what?
Not too shabby but
it ain't over yet.
Catch him!
Right!
You okay?
Other than being covered
in oil I'm just fine!
Incoming!
[JET] Here goes round two!
[JET screams]
[LEVY] Oh no, Jet!
Sorry, you guys...
My high speed is useless when
I'm all slicked up like this.
Looks like
it's up to me!
[DROY yells]
[stops yelling and pants]
[pants hard]
[yells]
I knew I should've
gone on a diet sooner.
They're both down.
Guess it's up to me!
Don't be stupid!
Let me handle this!
I'm perfectly capable
of handling this myself!
[GAJEEL yells]
I saw that one coming!
[PANTHERLILY] Taking a battle
form like this is strange
for an Exceed
born in Earth Land.
Yet it's the truth. I
was born in this world,
the same as your
friends Happy and Carla.
Then explain to me
why you chose to side
with the Legion Platoon!
Why do you refuse
to show compassion
for those who share
your circumstances?!
Zentopia took me in after
I was hatched and gave me
a place to call my own.
Lord Byro has been nothing
short of a father to me!
I owe everything
to Zentopia
and the Legion Platoon.
Repaying that debt is far
more important to me than
the Exceeds or Edolas!
Almost there!
So what now?
Damn! If we
don't get on top
of that thing,
we'll be at this forever!
Gajeel!
[SAMUEL] It's just as my
calculations predicted.
I will defeat you,
"Brother",
while the ancient guardian
takes care of your comrades.
And then, once the
dust has settled,
I will take the
clock piece at my leisure!
Fightin' on an empty
stomach ain't helpin'.
I need some iron and quick!
I guess I could bite
a chunk off of this thing.
We need that,
metal head!
Find something
else to munch on!
Cool it, princess, I was
just playin' around!!
Do you think we need
to be making jokes
at a time like this?
Run Gajeel!
It's trying to get the
clock piece back from us!
Ah, well that makes things
a lot easier. [chuckles]
You hold onto it!
[screams]
No, I don't wanna!
[yells]
Go get him!
He can't!
Dragon Slayer Secret Art...
Karmic Demon...
Iron God Sword!
Our business
here is done!
Finish yours up so we
can get outta this dump.
It's inconceivable!
How can this be?!
I've never once
come across anybody
who can elude my
calculations!
Perhaps they
were incorrect,
but if that's the case,
all my strategizing
was completely meaningless!
I can't take this!
It makes no sense!
A fight's a dynamic thing...
Strategy helps, but you
must be able to adapt
when things go wrong.
It looks to me like
you've still got
a lot of learning
to do, "Sammy."
My name is Samuel,
you troglodyte!
You've left
yourself open!
[bone cracking]
[groans]
Still, you are not
without talent...
If you challenge me
again in the future,
I'll be happy
to oblige you.
I know when it's time
to admit defeat.
And thanks to our fight,
I now realize there are
people in this world
who defy calculation.
So you've realized
your own inexperience?
On the contrary!
It's quite obvious that
I simply failed to anticipate
all of the variables!
Next time I'll be
sure to incorporate
every possible detail
into my calculations!
And then I'll show you
barbarians the power of
the only muscle
that truly matters!
But right now I need
to record every single bit
of data from this fight while
it's still fresh in my memory!
[punch]
[PANTHERLILY] Who're you
calling a barbarian, huh?!
Looks like Exceeds come in
all types too, don't they?
What's wrong? Miss him
already? "Brother"?
We're not related
in the slightest.
[ELFMAN] Check it out!
The lake is shrinking!
Guess Lisanna must've
found something down there.
[BOTH gasp]
Good work, Sis!
You found it!
I'm just glad that I
was able to be useful
for a change. I was beginning
to feel like a third wheel.
Silly, huh?
Nah, I noticed it, too.
[MIRAJANE] Okay! Let's grab
the clock piece and meet up
with the others!
It's heavy!
Manly throw!
What'd you do that for?!
Aw, not her!
[MARY] Thanks a lot, big guy.
I should thank all three
of you for helping me
get the clock piece without,
like, having to get wet.
[LISANNA]
Isn't she...?
[ELFMAN] Yeah, she's
that annoying girl
from the
Legion Platoon.
[MIRAJANE] Care to explain
how you knew where to find us?
I followed you here.
I figured it was easier
to let you find it,
and then totally steal it
right out from under you.
I'm, like, a genius!
Although, technically
I guess it was Samuel's idea.
Ha! Three against one?
Nice strategy!
Crap! I forgot!
You can try to fight it,
but that's not gonna help ya.
There's, like,
nothing you can do!
As long as I have this baton you
losers are totally my puppets!
[NATSU] Man, I can't believe
they're still goin' at it.
I dunno about you guys
but I'm gettin' hungry.
What part of "No!"
don't you get?!
"No!" doesn't exist in the
dictionary of love, Looeypie!
Creep! Perv!
Find someone else to try
and feel up!
You do realize that
she's not the only
girl down here, right?
Michelle is a proper young lady
with a body that won't quit,
if you know what I mean.
Hmmm...
Uh... hi.
I see what you're sayin';
she's pretty and all
but I like my girls to have
a little more life to 'em.
I don't get it; I
guess he's got a thing
for loud-mouthed tomboys.
Are you tryin' to
sneak in a jab, cat?
Shall I punish him
for you... Princess?
What the heck are you
doing here, Virgo?
I didn't summon you!
You know I'm always
ready, willing,
and able to offer my help
in your times of need.
Princess? I had no idea
Lucy was actually royalty!
Of course she is!
That explains why she's
so kind and beautiful!
[VIRGO] Princess... I could
put him deep in the ground
if that would please you.
[LUCY] Well that, uh... might...
be a... little... harsh.
Hello there. Are you
Loo-loo's maid?
In that case, I'd like
you to prepare a meal
for the two of us!
Something romantic to
kindle the fires of love!
I'm not ready to prepare
a meal, I'm afraid,
but I can entertain
you, if you'd like.
Not that again.
Wait a minute,
why are you listening to
him in the first place?!
I can't believe you
know my hometown's dance!
And you perform it with the
grace of a native to boot!
I've performed this
dance countless times before,
but I've never been
praised for it until now.
[LUCY] Hold on,
are they flirting?!
[HAPPY] Well, if you ask me,
they're perfect for each other.
It appears I've diffused
the situation, Princess.
If you need anything
else, let me know.
[LUCY] What...? I thought
you were getting rid of him!
[BYRO] How disappointing...
I expected you would have
the clock piece.
[DAN] That voice!
It's Lord Byro!
[NATSU] You mean,
the octo-jerk?!
[BYRO] I cannot understand
why the two of you seem
to be having such difficulty.
Our deepest apologies,
Lord Byro!
I'm terribly ashamed!
I allowed myself to become
distracted from my
objective; forgive me, sir!
However, I am happy to
report that this holy ground
is where I met the
girl of my dreams-
You deserved that.
Fall back and reflect
on your incompetence while
I clean up the
mess you've made.
Isn't that...?!
Mr. Jude's piece
of the clock!
Hey, Octo-geezer! That clock
hand belongs to Lucy!
[NATSU] Hand it over, or I'll
come up there and roast ya!
[HAPPY] And I'll scratch ya!
I warn you. You won't
live to regret it.
♪
[NATSU] What's with these
guys?! All we ever hear
from them is blah blah "holy
war", blah blah "clock piece."
[HAPPY] Well, They have
goals just like we do.
[NATSU] Whatever!
Just let me at 'em already!
[HAPPY] Let's just hope
they're all as simpleminded
as you are, huh?
[NATSU] If I didn't
know any better I'd say
you were insulting me.
[HAPPY] Whaddya mean?
It was a compliment!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
The Course of the Holy War!
Well, at least I'm not
a war monger, right?
[HAPPY] I would be if it gave
me a bigger role in the story.
[NATSU] Whoa...!
Sounds like somebody's
got their goals mixed up.