[NATSU] Previously,
on Fairy Tail!
[LUCY] Early into our
journey to gather the pieces
of a mysterious clock...
we stumbled upon a massive
tomb underneath the desert.
And of course,
given our horrible luck,
it's filled with booby traps!
♪
Aw man, not this clown!
How did you guys even find
out about this place?
Thanks to the "Key of
the Starry Heavens".
Samuel told me the
whole story from memory.
[DAN] And guess what?
It says there's a piece
of the clock right here.
It looks to me like you
sorry losers haven't been able
to find it yet, either.
[DAN] Hmm?
Could that really be my
lovely little Lulu pumpkin
over there?
Don't you ever call
me that again!
I guess she's
kinda pumpkiny.
That is quite a bit
more embarrassing than
the names from the last time.
Our paths were
meant to cross again...
Unavoidable destiny.
I can practically feel
the thread of fate
pulling us together!
How about you take that
thread and wrap it
around your
neck instead!
[DAN] L...!
O...!
V...!
E!
[NATSU] Well, I'd love to get
payback for last time...!
Fire Dragon... Roar!
I can't waste my time
screwin' around like this...
Because... love beckons me
with its sweet song!
Oh yeah!
Somebody help me!
My butt's on fire!
My butt's on fire!!!
[MICHELLE] I'll spank
it out for you!
Natsu, you need to
be more careful!
That shield is a real
big pain in the butt,
am I right?
[ROMEO] We gotta
get outta here!
[HAPPY] Footprints of the Myth!
[ROMEO] They're not
coming after us...
[MICHELLE] Oh, I hope we
were able to lose them!
[NATSU] Exactly like I planned!
[HAPPY] You're such a liar!
[LUCY] Let's just find
what we came here for!
Slooow down...! My
Lovely Lulu pumpkin.
First you and I need to
water our garden of love!
That has got to be the
craziest thing I've ever
heard in my life!
[COCO] Hold on! First, you and
I need to find that clock piece.
Have you already
forgotten that we were
sent here on an
important mission?
Did I forget my
mission? No way!
I remembered
my sweet love!
That's kinda
my point.
[DAN] L...!
O...!
V...!
E!
Would you stop?!
No my gorgeous,
delicate skin...
Your bottom's
on fire again!
Whoops, I'm sorry
about that, Lucy!
You dare stand in the
way of our love...?
For that I'll slice you up
like a tuna and serve you raw!
Sounds like a good
way to go to me!
[DAN] Now I'm gonna give you
another taste of my magic spear!
Open wide 'cause
here it comes!
[MICHELLE] You can't
let it hit you, Natsu!
Listen to her, if that
thing gets you again,
you're gonna go right
back to shrimpy mode!
Yeah, well duh...!
And that means you're gonna
step on me like last time!
[DAN] Good luck
dodging this...!
[MICHELLE] Lucy!
[high-pitched] Hey... Wait...!
No...! No...! NO...!
This isn't happening to me!
Oh crap, I missed!
I'm so sorry my love!
I never meant for this
to happen to you!
I've gone and shrunk
the love of my life!
How could I...?!
There's no way you'll want
me as your boyfriend now!
You're right, but
turn me back anyway!
Why, of course, my dear.
Hey, what's the hold up?
I kinda like this cute
little version of you.
Huh?!
You were smokin' hot
as a normal sized girl,
but now you're like the
cutest thing I've ever seen!
I wanna carry you with
me everywhere I go.
That is not
happening!
I'm just gonna
keep you like this
for a little while okay?
I got a special place
at home for you...
Then I can look at
you anytime I want!
I'm not some kind of
action figure, ya weirdo!
I'll hang you right here
and we'll always be together!
Whoa...!
He turned Lucy into some
kinda good luck charm!
Well, she is a whole
lot cuter like this!
Oh gosh, I want a
little Lucy, too!
Would you stop being
ridiculous and help me out here?
[DAN] Now that my tiny
beloved is by my side,
I have the heart of
a lion! I fear no man!
And thanks to her
my aim is true!
[COCO] Cut it out, Dan!
You can fight him later!
We need to find the
clock piece first!
Can't you see that
I'm busy right now?
Go on! I'm sure
you can find it!
I can't because Samuel
gave you all the details
about how to find it!
I don't even know where
to start looking!
What do we do? The whole
reason we came here
was to look for one of those
missing clock thingies, too!
But there's no way
we can leave Lucy behind
when she's so
tiny and helpless!
[LUCY] I'm gonna hurl unless
someone can make this stop...!
Hey wait!
Open! Gate
of the Archer!
Sagittarius!
How the diddley do
do you do, my lady?
Great googly moogly,
I've been turned
teensy weensy!
Pardon me!
All of my Spirits were
shrunk down, too?
What kinda crazy sense
does that make?!
Although I may be no
bigger than a doormouse,
I was still summoned to
my lady's side in her time
of great and dire need!
Therefore, I'll defend
her with all my might!
Whoa! Luck is
on my side today!
I've had this annoying little
fish bone stuck in my teeth
since lunch and it's been
driving me up the freakin' wall!
My mighty arrows
have been reduced
to toothpicks?
Never before in my life
have I experienced
such heart-breaking shame!
Thanks for your help,
'lil horse-man!
To return your kindness
I'll make this quick!
That's not necessary!
I can leave on
my own accord...
Get outta the
way, horsie!
Oh, my body!
Oh no! I did it again!
I think you're probably
better off goin' back home.
My complete and
utter failure here
has me saying
toodle-loo, my good lady!
That may have actually
made things worse.
I know!
Huh?
Normally, I'd never
dream of rushing
anybody into this,
but if you and Lucy
are meant to be together,
why don't you go ahead
and get married
right here?
Have you gone
completely insane?!
[MICHELLE] This place
is historic, sacred,
and romantic in its
own unique way...!
This could be
the perfect place!
[DAN] No, this is the
absolute most perfect place!
[LUCY] You know this is
some musty, old tomb, right?
This is going to be the
biggest day of your life
so we had better
start planning!
I'll do whatever it takes
to make it special!
[MICHELLE] First off,
we need to get the invitations
sorted out...
Some folks from your side,
some folks from her side...
Let's try to keep it intimate...
Maybe fifty guests?
[DAN] Yeah, A classy, intimate
ceremony is the only way to go!
[MICHELLE] And then you'll
travel around the world
on your honeymoon!
[DAN] A romance at sea!
[MICHELLE] Stories of your
undying love will inspire
future star-gazers to name a
constellation in your honor...!
"The Legendary Lovers"
will dominate the night sky!
This is amazing!
The sun is rising on our
glorious new life together!
Do I even have
a say here?
[DAN] L...!
O...!
V...!
E!
I can't take any more
of this lovey-dovey crap!
Are we gonna duke
it out or what?!
Now there's a stench
that'll ruin the mood.
Pee-yew!
Romeo, are you
causing that smell?
Yeah, I am.
Sorry.
but it's the only thing I could
think of trying that might help.
My god!
It smells like
hot sewage in here!
This cloud of
concentrated yuckiness
is setting my nostrils on fire!
No!
Our thread of fate
has been broken!
I got ya!
[LUCY] Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Not again!
Why does this keep
happening to me today?!
Hop on, Lucy!
I'll help you!
Hey! Give me back my
beautiful bride, cat!
Thanks! You're
a real life-saver!
Now, it's time to get
the heck outta here!
Aye, Sir!
All I have to do is turn
you back to normal size
and you'll fall to the ground
like a sexy sack of potatoes!
I'm back!
[MICHELLE] Whaaaa?!
[ROMEO] Whaaaa?!
[LUCY screams]
Uh-oh...
I guess my hand must have
slipped a little bit.
Wow! Happy
is a giant!
You suck at
that, ya know!
Yeah, he's right!
You should really learn
how to use that thing
before ya go whippin'
it out, ya moron!
I'm way too big, you
guys! I can't get out!
No! Please!
Happy! Stop!
Sorry! I didn't mean
to squish you again.
I'm starting to
think that you might
be doing this
on purpose, buddy.
Are you sure there's
not an easier way
to get where we're going?
Hate to break it
to ya but according
to the map we're following,
this is the only way!
If we were traveling
on flat ground,
I could get there in no time...
But all this climbing is
a huge pain in the butt!
Hey Lily, why don't you
do your teammates a favor
and fly us to the top
of this stupid thing?!
If I do that, we run
the risk of missing any
important clues we might
find along the way.
We simply can't afford
to take the easy way out!
Either stop with
all your whinin'
or get left behind!
As soon as we're there,
I'm gonna kill him.
[ERZA] Hmm... It would appear
we took a wrong turn somewhere.
It feels as if we've
been wandering around
aimlessly all day,
if ya ask me.
Don't you have the
directions to get there?
I have a map but the
details are extremely vague.
I'm afraid that we're
just going to have to rely
on these road signs
to show us the way.
[CARLA] That's all well and
good, but can anybody tell me
which direction this sign
is actually pointing?
Now that you mention it,
it is a bit confusing.
Yes, to say the least...
You don't suppose that
this could be somebody's
sick idea of a prank?
[CANA] That'd be a really
crappy thing to do...
Besides, isn't it a crime to
change the direction of a sign?
One wrong turn could put
somebody in real danger.
We should at least
be getting closer...
Let's proceed with caution
while checking the map as well.
Is it really just
a random prank?
Or could it be someone
deliberately trying
to steer us
off course?
[HAPPY screams]
Stop flying
around, Happy!
If I get back on the
ground, I'm afraid
I'm gonna squish somebody!
I know these are ruins,
but they're part of
Fiore's history! We can't
afford to ruin them any further!
I'm more afraid of these
rocks ruining my skull!
[DAN] Alright, you
overgrown flea-bag!
[HAPPY screams]
Quit freakin' out,
you're normal.
Everyone's finally
back to regular size!
We gotta find that
missing clock piece.
I hated bein'
a monster!
[ROMEO] But how are we
gonna find the stupid thing
if we don't even know
where to start looking?
Don't worry...
I brought the book along with
me to help us figure out
some more clues.
I have no doubt it'll point us
in the right direction at least.
[COCO] If we get our
hands on that book,
we could find the
piece in no time!
So hand it over, blondie!
Get back!
Hey now!
[LUCY] This is our chance!
You can't run from us!
[NATSU] Good, cause I ain't
runnin'! I'm stayin' right here!
'Cause I still owe you
a serious butt kickin'!
Thanks for holding
him off, Natsu!
Just try not to let
him step on you again!
The only one who ever
stepped on me was you!
[COCO] Get back here!
If you stand in my
way be prepared to pay
the ultimate price!
I'm ready to settle
the score once and for all!
I've got you now!
No you don't!
So where's the
piece?! Have you
figured it out yet?!
I'm still
looking. Uhhh...
[bonk]
[LUCY screams]
[rumbling]
[COCO] Aw man! I guess I
ran out of magic power...
[LUCY] Hold this!
[LUCY] Grab
my hand!
I can't accept
an enemy's mercy!
Would you quit being
so darn stubborn?!
[gasps]
[relieved sigh]
[BOTH moan and groan]
[MICHELLE] Oh no,
Lucy! Are you okay?!
I'm still alive,
at least!
[ROMEO] Hang on! We're
coming down to help you!
[LUCY] No, don't
worry about me...!
You guys just hurry up
and find that clock piece!
We'll meet up
eventually, I'm sure!
[MICHELLE] Oh, I'm
worried about her...
I mean, she's stuck down there
with that horrible little girl.
[HAPPY] Well, she does have her
Celestial Spirits with her too,
so she'll probably be fine.
Yeah. Let's go. We can't
help her from up here anyway.
[MICHELLE] We'll find it
Lucy! But please be careful!
[LUCY] Yeah, you too!
Owie...
Hey... are you hurt?
You get away from me!
In case you didn't notice,
your so-called "help" is
how we got stuck down here
in the first place!
You better watch
your mouth little girl,
unless you wanna end up
someplace a whole lot worse!
I can't think of any
place worse than being trapped
down here with you!
What is with
the attitude? Ya know,
I once met someone who looks
and sounds a lot like you;
except she wasn't such a brat!
[COCO] Wow...
What a great story.
Obviously that wasn't me,
so get over it!
So... what exactly
is the Legion Platoon's
goal here anyway? Why're
you trying to collect
all the clock pieces?
What's with all this
"holy war" and "chaos" stuff?!
Well, I got a
question for you!
If you don't know
what we're doing,
then why are you and your
friends trying to stop us?
We're trying to figure
everything out, that's all...
Why? Is there something
else we should be doing?
Yeah, how about
leaving us alone?!
You guys are nothin' but
a bunch of crappy wizards.
You might as well give
up while you still can.
[LUCY] Isn't she
a ray of sunshine?
We need to be careful...
There's probably a lot more
of those booby
traps everywhere.
I know, genius! The
builders put them here
to stop grave robbers
like you and your buddies.
You're here for the exact
same reason as we are!
[COCO] Look out!
Thanks...
You saved my life!
There's need to thank me.
You tried to save me earlier,
I'm returning the favor
by actually saving you.
Are you seriously this
unfriendly all of the time?
It's weird because you're
so much like the other
Coco I know... Except
she's a million times nicer.
That so? Well then,
how am I like this other girl?
[LUCY] Besides
your personality,
you two are
practically identical.
[COCO] What?
Like I was saying earlier,
she looks and sounds
exactly like you, and
we actually started out
as enemies, too. But by the
end, she'd become one of
my closest friends.
That sounds
nothing like me.
Because I would never
be friends with a stupid
wannabe wizard like you!
You don't have
to get so personal;
we're just worried putting the
clock together is gonna cause
major some problems.
We're trying to stop a worldwide
disaster from happening.
You know, the whole
"inevitable chaos" thing?
Do you guys honestly
think we want
to destroy the world?
We really don't
know what you want.
Personally, I'm just hoping
to try and understand
what in the heck my dad
was tryin' to tell me.
Yeah, your dad...
You're the daughter of
Jude Heartfilia, aren't you?
He was one of the richest
businessmen in the country.
[LUCY] I may be his daughter,
but I can't say that we ever
saw eye-to-eye on much.
And this is no exception;
I mean, why would anybody go
to all the trouble to
hide pieces of a clock
in all these weird,
hard to find places?
I can't help thinking
there had to be an easier way
to go about it.
That may be the one
thing we agree on.
[amused sigh]
You wanna tell
me what's so funny?!
Nothing! Well, I was
actually just thinking
that you're kind
of silly, that's all.
Hey, I don't appreciate
you saying that about me.
Sorry, I didn't mean
it as an insult... Hold on.
It's a dead-end.
You think maybe we should
turn around and go back?
Geez... You don't
know anything, do ya?
Places like this always
have secret hidden exits.
[LUCY] No! Don't touch that!
[rumbling]
[crash]
Coco!
Oh my gosh!
Are you okay?!
[HAPPY] Lucy!
Thank goodness you're
alive! I was so worried!
Hey!
Come over here and
we can pull you up!
I probably would've just
left her there if I were you.
Yeah, but that just
didn't feel right to me.
According to the
information Lucy gave us...
we should be sitting on top
of one of the clock pieces
right about now.
Hmmm...
If that's the case,
how come nobody's seen it yet?
[groans and panting]
I was afraid we'd
never get up that cliff.
The air's so
thin up here.
Not to mention
super cold.
You creampuffs better
get over it. Now c'mon...
Move your butts.
Will you let us catch
our breath for a minute?
I don't even think
I can move right now.
I gotta eat
somethin'.
Oh no, I think we climbed
the wrong mountain!
The clock piece is on
that mountain over there!
Looks like we've got
more climbing to do!
[ALL] Say what??!!
[chuckles] I'm just kidding
but those looks are priceless.
[smirks]
Huh?
[PANTHERLILY] I was trying
to lighten the mood with
a little humor, but I guess it
backfired. Learn to take a joke.
[GAJEEL] I'm still not
seein' any clock pieces.
Which means... the
stupid thing's probably
buried up here
somewhere, I'll bet.
So what do we do now?
We're here! We've
finally found it!
The Library of Sorcery
holds countless texts
on almost every type of magic
that's ever been practiced.
It's quite impressive.
[CANA] Yeah, no joke. The
place is freakin' humongous.
[WENDY] But it doesn't
look like anybody's
been here in a long time.
That's a real tragedy.
All that knowledge just
waiting to be learned.
[gasps]
[CANA] You're tellin' me all
these books are about magic?!
What a wonderful sight
to behold, don't you think?
Yeah, We should come
back here sometime
and bring Levy.
My word! So many books
full of ancient wisdom.
[gasps]
[shock]
[confused sound]
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Roar!
Take this!
[DAN] I'm sick and tired
of messin' around with you!
I could say the same
thing to you, pal.
Then let's end this.
Prepare to die!
The time has come for
me put your fire out
once and for all!
You'll never beat me!
♪
[NATSU sniffs]
[NATSU] Man, that smell
is really familiar.
[HAPPY] What smell?
[NATSU] It's weird...
It's either from somebody
who helped me when
I was feelin' sick...
Or from somebody
who attacked me.
[HAPPY] Those are
totally different things!
So which one is it?
Is it a good guy
smell or bad guy smell?
[NATSU] It's the smell of
someone who's pretty harmless,
but acts like a
really bad guy?
[NATSU and HAPPY] Next time:
True Scoundrels, Once Again!
[HAPPY] Hmm... So, what
does that smell like?
[NATSU] I guess it's kinda
like a black unitard...
[HAPPY] That doesn't sound
like a good smell to me!