I don't understand
what happened.
I thought Mavis said the plan
was to keep Blue Skull's
leader trapped in this cage.
Maybe she just forgot to
lock it up? Seems odd.
My friends. I hope
everyone is all right.
[roars]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[ZERA]
Precht!
Have you seen Mavis?
Ugh!
I must say I'm impressed
by the illusions
you're able to create.
Did you teach yourself that?
I did.
But my illusions are useless
in a battle with wizards.
I wanna learn the kind of
spells that can help me fight!
If I understand correctly,
you're asking me to
teach you black magic.
I'm not concerned whether
it's black or white magic.
It doesn't matter. I just want
to take down Blue Skull.
[MAVIS]
Here goes!
Mommy! Look, gold coins!
They're falling from the sky!
What the hell is goin' on here?!
At long last, the day I've
dreamed about has come!
[MAN A]
What amazing timing!
[BOY A laughing]
So pretty!
Hey, no fair!
What? They vanished.
Mavis did this. It's her magic.
[MAN D]
It's coming back for us!
[MAN C]
Run for your lives!
Everybody get to safety.
The gold is just an illusion!
I get it! Mavis is
trying to distract Yuri!
[PRECHT] Even if he
turns into a monster,
a treasure hunter will
always be attracted
by the sparkle of gold.
[sighs]
This is it.
[roars]
[MAVIS yelps]
Okay. This is close enough.
I can use Law from here!
[ZERA]
Don't do it, Mavis!
Zera! You shouldn't
be up here with me!
I came up to remind you
what the teacher told you
about using that spell!
He said that it would take you
at least ten years to master it!
And you promised him you would
never use it until then!
He said that the
price of casting it
before you were ready
would be terrible!
Don't take that chance!
I know that.
But Law is an
ancient super-spell
based on absolute
purity of judgment.
It saves what the caster thinks
is good and destroys evil.
Using this spell now might be
my only chance to save Yuri
and destroy the Tenrou
Orb's evil energy.
But not if you haven't
even mastered it yet!
I know how risky it is,
but right now it's
our only option!
[screams]
Mavis, no!
Oh, no, Mavis!
[roars]
[ZERA] Mavis! Don't do it,
I'm begging you!
I don't have any other choice!
Please think this through!
Unless my chances of saving Yuri
from this evil are
absolutely zero,
I'll do anything to help him!
No spell is too risky when
a friend's life is at stake!
Do you have to put
your life at stake?
I do, Zera.
Before we met those three,
we were trapped on that island.
They showed us a world
we had only dreamed of.
Precht is someone we
can always count on,
who cares about his friends.
Warrod knows just how to bring
out the best in everyone.
We need them!
After all that we've
been through together,
I can't let our adventure
end like this!
So I'll do whatever I can
to keep us together!
But, Mavis...
Beyond that, it's
something I can't explain.
I'm not sure what makes me care
so deeply about those guys.
But I have a feeling
in my heart.
And I think this is the
meaning of friendship!
It's friendship?
[MAVIS]
So I'm begging you, Zera!
Please get away from here
before it's too late!
It's too dangerous!
Zera, no!
Don't forget that
I'm your friend, too.
[ZERA] Hey, Mavis. Do you
still believe in fairies?
Of course I do.
I know that they're real.
I believe in them too,
but I believe in you even more.
When this is over, let's look
for fairies together.
All of us.
[roars]
[ZERA]
Mavis!
[MAVIS] You've given me so much
courage over the years, Zera.
I never would have
made it this far...
...If it weren't for you!
I can't thank you enough!
Are you saying that you
meant to jump up there?
[MAVIS]
Yes! Precisely as I calculated!
[MAVIS] I corrected for the
ether-nano density in the air,
the wind, and the temperature.
I worked it out to be here
at this exact moment.
[MAVIS]
One.
Two.
Three.
[MAVIS]
Law!
[PEOPLE gasping]
[footsteps]
Her plan actually worked!
You really pulled it off, Mavis!
Your spell was able to
save Yuri and Magnolia!
Hey, Mavis!
Where are you?
Mavis!
[gasps]
Mavis.
No. No, please.
Stop it! Come on!
Quit joking around!
Please wake up!
[ZERA]
Mavis!
[ZERA crying]
[ZERA] Don't do this!
Please! Don't die!
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAKO] Is there anything
you can do for her, Doctor?
She saved our whole
city from the dragon!
So you gotta save her!
She is gonna pull
through this, right, doc?
I wish I could give you
all a definitive answer,
but even I don't understand
why she won't wake up.
Poor Mavis.
We can run some tests,
but I'm afraid there's not
much else we can do here.
The only thing we
know for certain
is that using that
incredible spell
is what put her in this state.
Did you bring your kid brother
in here dressed as a doctor?!
We get that the spell
knocked her out,
but what I wanna know is
why she ain't wakin' up!
Like we've already told
you several times,
we don't have any idea!
Agh! You jerks are nothin'
but a bunch of useless quacks!
What? How dare you
speak to me that way...!
Hands off!
[MAN B]
Calm down, you two!
Please, Miss Mavis. Wake up.
[KERSEY] Well, your best
ain't good enough, is it?
Who do you think
you are anyway?
[PEOPLE arguing]
[WOMAN A] The citizens of
Magnolia owe her our lives!
Please, do everything you can!
[MAN C]
The people of our city
want to express our
gratitude to Mavis.
Let us know if we can
do anything to help.
Please, we don't have much time!
Yes, yes. You just calm
right down, young man.
[OLD HAG A] Looks like this
must've been a real disaster.
Yeah.
I can still feel it.
The traces of an immense
spell remain in this place.
I'm back. How's Mavis doing?
She still hasn't
opened her eyes.
Who might this be?
She's one of the elders from
a nearby town's wizard guild.
I'm basically a doctor
who specializes
in treating wizards
injured by magic.
Now, let me have a look.
Well, this little thing
brought down a giant dragon?
I can't believe someone so young
used such a tremendous spell.
That great blast of
light was visible
all the way over in our town.
We all saw it.
Well? Is she all right?
Say something!
Hey! Stop it!
Let her concentrate.
What's wrong?
This worse than I
could have imagined.
What is it?
Please, you have to tell us!
It's a good thing Yuri
isn't awake. Considering.
Yeah, that poor guy.
He's gonna have one heck of a
wake up call, that's for sure.
[PRECHT] Well, I just hope he
doesn't take the news too hard.
Welcome back to the
land of the living.
[YURI]
Where are we?
[WARROD]
An inn, in Magnolia.
[PRECHT]
Yuri! You're awake!
Are you feeling all right?
Yeah.
[YURI groans]
[PRECHT]
What's the matter?
Oh, it's probably nothing.
I just have a really killer
headache, that's all.
That makes sense,
considering what happened.
The Tenrou Orb's curse
took you over completely.
It was ugly.
[gasps]
Where's Mavis?
Please say something.
Where is she?
[WARROD] Well, technically,
she isn't harmed.
But she had to use an
insanely powerful spell.
It was the only way
to break the curse.
[PRECHT] All of the doctors
in the city examined her,
and no one could do anything.
We even brought in a specialist
from a nearby wizard guild.
What are you getting at?
Why won't you tell me
what's happened to her?!
[PRECHT] We're telling
you everything we know.
Just calm down and listen.
[PRECHT]
The specialist said that this is
the price she must pay for
using such a dangerous spell
before having mastered it.
[PRECHT]
Mavis' body won't grow anymore.
She'll stay as small as she is
now for the rest of her life.
Yuri!
Thank goodness! I'm so
glad to see you awake!
But how? How can
you be so happy?
You'll never grow because of me.
Nothing that happened
is your fault.
I knew there were risks,
and I don't regret it.
I'm just grateful
that you're all right.
I don't deserve it. You didn't
have to do this for me!
I did.
You're my friend, and I would
do it again in a heartbeat.
Don't say that!
This whole time I was just
trying to get to the orb!
I was using you.
[YURI cries]
[YURI]
Forgive me. Please.
I'm so sorry, Mavis.
Please don't cry.
It's not like you.
[YURI]
So you're not hurt or anything?
I'm not.
I never felt an instant of pain
throughout all that happened.
I won't grow anymore,
but other than that I'm fine.
[YURI]
Listen.
When I was under the
Tenrou Orb's control,
I was certain I
heard your voice.
[MAVIS]
What?
I still hear it. You said
we're friends, always.
I meant it. That's how I feel.
Yeah, me too.
After all we've been
through together,
I could never call you
anything but my friend.
You really mean that?
Once things have quieted down,
you and me, we should go
look for fairies together.
[MAVIS]
What?
Are you totally sure
you're okay, Yuri?
You're not just saying that
'cause you feel guilty, are you?
[YURI]
No.
You're not like anyone
I've ever met.
I feel like just the same
as with Precht and Warrod,
I can trust you with my heart.
There are very few truly
trustworthy people
in this world.
[YURI] You risked your
life to save mine.
I wanna repay you by helping
you realize your dream.
Well, thank you.
But I want you to
find your own dream
and pursue that for yourself.
It's your life.
Well, from now on,
my dream is to always protect
you, no matter the cost.
To trust you and put
all my faith in you.
You and I may have come
from different worlds...
...but I'll be beside
you for life.
Thanks!
[YURI]
There's more, Mavis.
Because I'm your friend...
...there's something
that I have to tell you.
[MAVIS]
Huh?
[YURI]
It's about Zera.
[MAVIS]
What do you mean? Is she okay?
[YURI]
Zera. You're listening, right?
Zera! Why were you hiding again?
I can't believe you would
still be so shy around Yuri.
[MAVIS]
What's wrong?
Mavis.
[MAVIS]
Yes?
I've never been
able to see Zera.
[MAVIS]
Huh...?
[YURI]
And I can't hear her speak.
At all.
And it's not just me.
The other guys can't either.
None of us have ever
seen or heard her.
I'm sorry to have
to tell you this now.
[MAVIS gasps]
[YURI] You're the only one
who can perceive her.
Because she's an
illusion you created.
She's not real.
[MAVIS] Zera is an illusion
I created out of loneliness.
All I can do is cry in the
face of this shocking news.
She died that night
when we were children.
As Zera fades away,
she leaves me with
words of encouragement
so I can move forward on my own.
The story that began with a girl
who had less than zero
reaches its conclusion,
and I go forth on a new path.
Next Time: "Eternal Adventure."
The tale of the beginning
comes to an end.