[FUTURE ROGUE] Yes, that's it!
Good work, my minions!
Rampage and tear the city apart!
Show them the unadulterated
rage of dragons!
It's you. Natsu Dragneel.
You fool. It's hopeless.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Yet you refuse to die.
[grunts]
[NATSU yells]
[HAPPY] Seven Dragons!
[FUTURE ROGUE chuckles]
[NATSU grunts]
[FUTURE ROGUE] Come now,
do you truly believe
those paltry flames
of yours could ever harm me?
[NATSU grunts]
All those battles
have taken their toll.
You've almost completely
exhausted your resources.
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Struggle all you like,
you've no chance of victory.
[NATSU] There's no way
in hell I'm gonna
give up without a fight!
Shake off that parasite!
[yelling]
You're wasting your energy!
[groans]
[NATSU] Nice try, pal!
[NATSU grunts]
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Your tenacity is remarkable,
but ultimately pointless!
[panting]
[FUTURE ROGUE]
The city is doomed!
[NATSU groans]
[roars]
[FUTURE ROGUE chuckles]
It will soon be nothing more
than a pile of rubble and ash!
What are you trying to
accomplish with all of this?
Tell me!
One-zero-zero-nine-seven-seven.
As much as I hate to admit it,
he may indeed
prove useful at this time.
But are you certain
we can trust the words
of a criminal such as Jellal?
I have my doubts.
Me too. But.
He did make an extremely
convincing argument.
Given his tarnished history,
we must proceed with caution.
Is this just another scheme?
There's simply no other choice.
Trusting him is
our only option now.
[DORANBOLT] The fate
of humanity is at stake.
[roars]
Has the city's
evacuation been completed?
Yeah. Just about done.
They're safe. The Royal
Army is protecting them.
Aw, yeah! And that
means we can start to
let loose on
these stupid lizards!
It's about time for some
ultra-manly pest control!
There are seven dragons.
What do you suggest
we do first, master?
I'm not sure.
But it's clear...
we must do whatever
we can to neutralize them.
I'm worried about little Asca
being so close
to the front lines.
You're being very quiet, child.
Aren't you scared?
[ATLAS FLAME roars]
[MAVIS] I imagine
her fear is being
overwhelmed by fascination.
Laying eyes on a dragon
is a unique experience.
One that she will never
forget and will have
a profound impact
on her growth as a wizard.
I'll protect her. But she
should stay here for now.
We'll leave if we need to.
I understand. Watch over her.
Looks like a fire dragon to me.
What do you say
we take him on, Juvia?
Yes, my darling.
A monster like this
is no match for our love.
We're a force of nature.
Raaah! Okay, you and I
need to have a serious talk!
But now's really not the time.
Let's go!
--[JUVIA] Right!
--[GRAY] I need you to focus!
[BOTH yell]
All right!
Now hit him hard, you guys!
Show that flaming freak
what a man can do!
Ice Make: Geyser!
Water Nebula!
[ATLAS FLAME growls]
It didn't do anything!
No way! We combined our
burning passion for each other
and hit it with
our full magic power!
[ATLAS FLAME]
Foolish creatures!
I am the mighty Atlas Flame.
My fire consumes
all that stands before me!
Now prepare to have
your lives burned away!
I'll nullify it!
With my Enchantment magic!
[FRIED groans]
[MACAO, KINANA,
ELFMAN, and CANA yell]
[ERZA, WARREN,
and ROMEO groan, yell]
[JUVIA, GRAY,
and MAX groan, yell]
[BIXLOW] He blasted
through Fried's spell
like it was nothing!
It's way stronger than
I feared. This is insane!
What's really insane is there
are six more of those things!
We cannot lose hope!
We have to keep fighting!
Is everyone okay?
You gotta be kiddin' me!
This is just like what we
went through with Acnologia!
I hope this ends differently.
It would appear that
we have a long and
dangerous struggle ahead of us.
Don't worry.
We still have a couple of
tricks up our sleeves.
[ATLAS FLAME] Still standing
after the roasting I gave you?
You must be wizards!
[MAKAROV] Damn right we are!
[ERZA] Master!
[JUVIA]
What are you going to do?
[growls]
Oh wow! That's a great idea!
Fight a monster with a monster.
He's gonna give him a good
old-fashioned smack down!
Aw yeah! Awesome!
I haven't seen this
in a long time!
[MAKAROV yelling]
Fairy Tail are
no ordinary wizards!
[MAKAROV] The power we share
is like none other!
Because we are a family!
[ALL groan]
[grunts]
All that power
and nothing?
It didn't even faze him!
No way.
[ATLAS FLAME]
There is nothing you can do!
Humans will never
defeat a dragon!
[MAKAROV grunts]
[ALL yell]
Take this, Kitten Blast!
It's useless.
Sorry guys.
But our magic is just
no match for this thing.
Argh, this sucks!
Perhaps you should
fall back for now.
A girl like you
is only going to get hurt.
Meow? What the heck
do ya mean by that, you pig?
As I remember,
you weren't much of
a force to be reckoned with
back in the arena!
[LYON] That was
just for entertainment
so I was holding back.
This is a life or death battle.
Ice Make. Snow Dragon!
[HIBIKI] That's right!
We've got our own dragon!
[OHBA] Great idea, Lyon!
But since I didn't think of it,
I have to keep on spinning!
I'm not done!
Ice Make: Ape!
[LYON] Ice Make: Snow Tiger!
Three beasts at once.
The very same technique
he used in our battle.
Yes, we can outnumber it!
[LYON] Huh? If you'll recall,
this technique alone wasn't
enough for me to win the match.
I'll help you!
Miss Kagura! Join with us!
Let's go!
If we work together,
we can take this beast down!
[roars]
I shall draw
my Archenemy Blade.
And even though it may shatter,
my fighting spirit
will never be broken!
I am prepared
to use my full power!
In the sacred name
of my master Ur,
I will not give up!
[ALL grunt]
We're all counting
on you! Fight!
Give him every ounce
of strength you have!
We can't let that monster win!
[JURA, LYON, and KAGURA yell]
--[JURA and KAGURA groan]
--[LYON yells]
[ALL grunt]
[MILLIANNA] Meow!
That didn't hurt him at all!
What do we do?
Keep fighting! We cannot
afford to give up any ground!
It's up to us
to protect the city!
I would never dream
of surrendering!
[ZIRCONIS] Ooh. They are
really goin' at it aren't they?
You humans have
always been entertaining!
[laughs]
It's Zirconis.
This is crazy.
I could swear that he was
a ghost the last time that
we ran into him, wasn't he?
Yeah, and it seems
like he's just as much
of a loudmouth
in the flesh.
[ZIRCONIS]
Why are you so surprised?
I'm not the type to just
mindlessly destroy everything,
like some of
these other dragons.
I'm a great conversationalist.
Not to brag too much, but
I've always been a bit more
intellectual and sophisticated
than most of my brethren.
But you're all trembling,
completely frozen with fear.
I do strike terror
into your hearts, don't I?
If ya wanna run,
I reckon now's your chance.
That just means I'll have to
chase you down to eat ya!
Please, tell me something!
[ZIRCONIS] Ah. What is this?
You wanna have a chat
with me, little girl?
Why did you all come here?
Why are you destroying
our home like this?
[ZIRCONIS] Ya wanna know why?
To tell ya the truth,
that's who ya should be askin'.
Ya see Mother Glare
flyin' around up there?
Well, that guy
perched on top is the one
who's callin' all
the shots on this thing.
[WENDY] That's the Rogue who
came from the future, isn't it?
[ZIRCONIS]
Oh, don't get me wrong,
no human's gonna boss me around.
But this was a pretty fun idea,
so I went along with it.
[LUCY] I don't get it.
Why would he want these dragons
to destroy the world like this?
I mean, if they're
really able to do it,
then he won't have
anywhere to call home either.
[SERENA] Oh, Mister Doranbolt.
I've been expecting you, sir.
[DORANBOLT] You've told
no one about this, right?
[SERENA] Of course not.
[DORANBOLT] One-zero-zero-
nine-seven-seven is this way?
[SERENA] Yes sir.
But, we really don't have
the proper authorization
to be here right now.
This is a dire situation.
We don't have the time to
go through all the red tape.
I'll take full responsibility.
But sir. There are certain
rules that need to be--
[SERENA]
What are you doing?
[groans]
I'm sorry. But time
is of the essence.
[footsteps]
Attention.
One-zero-zero-nine-seven-seven.
[MAN scoffs] So it is you.
I thought I could
hear you comin' for me.
[roars]
So this is the power
a dragon possesses.
A sight I'm certain
I shall never forget.
This is perfect. I got
knocked outta that last round
way quicker than I thought.
I'm ready to throw down!
I'll blow this critter away!
Lightning God
Charged Particle Cannon!
As tribute to Gray Fullbuster,
and his decisive
victory over me,
I'll fight this foul
creature using Ice Magic.
[RUFUS] Memory Make.
Sword of Frozen Black Lightning!
[bellows]
I never thought I'd see
those two work together.
I mean we were
in the same guild,
but things definitely
weren't like this!
Perhaps their
experiences in the games
have taught them something.
Sabertooth is finally
fightin' like a real team!
Everybody was just goin' out
for themselves before.
This is awesome!
Yeah, it's totally awesome!
Yep, watching those
Fairy Tail guys in action
was a real eye opener.
There's a good reason they
came in first place this year!
Memorizing is
a form of learning.
And if you can't learn from
your enemy, you will never win.
I think that
they're gonna beat it!
Yeah they are!
[roars]
But we hit that thing full on!
That's impossible!
How is it still standing?
Get back, Frosch
and Lector. Do it now!
[LECTOR] Okay!
[FROSCH] Wait for me!
Just where in the hell
did Milady go?
We could use
her help right now!
I don't know. I haven't
seen her in a while.
But I assume she's
fighting somewhere else.
Can we even beat this monster?
I think it should be possible.
If memory serves me,
Sting and Rogue both
killed dragons
when they were young.
Well, you're half right.
[WEISSLOGIA]
Sting. Please, end my life.
I can't do that!
Please don't make me.
[WEISSLOGIA] Those who
wield Dragon Slaying magic
grow stronger once they've
bathed in dragon's blood.
[YOUNG STING]
No. I'm not gonna do it!
[WEISSLOGIA] You must!
Prove you've mastered
the skills I've taught you!
[YOUNG STING crying]
[STING scoffs]
Skiadrum had been suffering
from a serious illness,
so all I did, was just
put him out of his misery.
I didn't realize
that's what happened.
It must be a memory filled
with great sorrow for you.
But if you can kill dragons,
now is definitely
the time to do it!
These guys are
way more powerful!
I don't even know
if we can kill 'em!
But we still have to try!
We have to protect our friends!
[FUTURE ROGUE] I told you
earlier that in seven years,
dragons would reign
supreme over this world,
obliterating everything!
[FUTURE ROGUE] However,
it won't be ruled by these
that you see before you today!
[NATSU] So the ones
that're tearin' stuff up
ain't gonna be in charge?
[FUTURE ROGUE] That's right.
Seven years from now,
there will be
only one creature that
sits on top of the food chain.
You've encountered him before.
The black dragon, Acnologia!
There's no way in hell.
Many wizards tried
to take him down,
but all were slain.
And there are no more
guilds to speak of.
They've been eradicated.
[FUTURE ROGUE] I created a
spell for controlling dragons,
but it had no effect
on Acnologia.
[gasps]
[ZIRCONIS]
Despite his human origins,
he became the King
of all dragon kind.
His name was Acnologia.
Once a human being,
now a dragon,
cloaked in wings of darkness.
And now he can only be defeated
by dragons led by me!
That's the reason you
summoned all these dragons?
You're right again!
[FUTURE ROGUE] I traveled
seven years across time.
My plan was to
convince Princess Hisui
to open the Eclipse and
summon countless dragons
through that portal.
I only managed to get
a few dragons across
before that meddlesome
Lucy Heartfilia got in my way!
[FUTURE ROGUE] But because
of my skill in using
Dragon Tamer Magic,
I have total control
of all who did pass through.
[FUTURE ROGUE] Acnologia
doesn't stand a chance
against me now.
And once I slay
that black-winged tyrant,
I will be the true Dragon King!
[NATSU] No you won't!
How I've been dreaming
for such power!
It's within my grasp!
I only smell seven dragons.
So that's it, huh?
Seven dragons
are all that I need!
The world will
soon belong to me!
You gotta have some
seriously rotten luck, pal.
Say what?
[KAGURA grunts]
Kagura! Are you all right?
I will be just fine.
Don't worry about me!
[OHBA] I'm just gonna
go right ahead and keep on
spinning and spinning
and spinning and spinning
and spinning
and spinning and--!
Would those who have been
injured please step forward?
[JURA] Shelia will help you!
Find anything? Does that
tell you what we can do
to stop the dragons?
I'm still working on it!
I think the only way
is attacking them
with the full force
of Dragon Slayer magic.
[roars]
[STING] You're right,
it's the only hope we have left!
We can't just
go down without a fight!
Let's do it! It's up to us!
We're Dragon Slayers, so let's
show the world what that means.
[MACAO and WAKABA] Master!
Are you okay?
Did it hurt you?
No need to worry.
I just got a little
burned is all.
If not even
the master could stop it,
then the rest of us
don't stand a chance.
Vile creature!
There has got to be
some other way!
[GRAY] Master Mavis! You're a
wiz with strategy, aren't ya?
So what do you
think we should do?
Listen up!
There are seven dragons.
[MAVIS] The plan
of action should be
completely obvious
at this point!
Huh?
What are you
trying to say?
[growls]
Where does luck play into this?
This is about skill!
[FUTURE ROGUE gasps]
[bellows]
[roars]
What are you doing?!
Can you hear me?
[NATSU]
Let's quit playin' around
and use our Dragon Slayer magic!
Is that Natsu?
Oh yeah!
I hear ya.
There are seven dragons!
[NATSU] And we got
seven Dragon Slayers!
We can do this!
It's what we were born for!
Our whole lives
have led to this day!
Let's use our powers and
slay some freakin' dragons!
Damn you!
Who's with me?
[NATSU] 'Cause I'm
goin' dragon hunting!
[FUTURE ROGUE]
Seven Dragon Slayers?
I'm afraid you're short by one!
I can hear the last one comin'!
[panting]
I appreciate you
going through the trouble.
[DORANBOLT] It's okay.
He's here with us now.
Dragons are
attacking the city.
Ya don't say?
I already heard.
We need your power.
So will you help us?
I hear ya up there, Natsu.
Loud and clear.
[chcukles]
[HAPPY] You remember Zirconis?
That dragon ghost
that we talked to?
[NATSU] Oh yeah, all he wanted
to talk about was food, right?
[HAPPY] That's not all
he talked about!
Anyway, apparently
he's got some kinda
super scary magic that strips
humans of their dignity!
[NATSU] Really?
Then you're probably cool
if he didn't mention cats.
[HAPPY] Well, I'm not
so sure about that.
[NATSU] Ooh! Why don't
we test it and see?
[HAPPY] No way! Are you crazy?
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next time: Zirconis' Magic!
[HAPPY] Well, I bet it
wouldn't work on you either
'cause you're like super human!
[NATSU] I'm not
gonna test it either!