[gasps]
The Alegria swallowed
up many lives just now.
But one seems to have
avoided its grasp.
[LUCY grunting]
Oww!
[LUCY] What is all this?
It looks like some
kind of tissue.
The chance of surviving
that curse is less than one
in a billion. What fortune.
Tragic.
One solitary human soul left
to suffer in the underworld.
[LUCY]
Everything's different.
Natsu? Where are you?!
[rumbling]
[GIANT CUBE growls]
[CROWD whimpering]
[MAN A]
That square thing grew a mouth!
[MAN B]
It's a monster!
[WOMAN A] Is that what
destroyed the guildhall?
[GIANT CUBE growls]
[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD screams]
[GIANT CUBE roars]
[MAN C]
Kardia Cathedral! No!
[MAN D]
Run for your lives!
[MAN E] It's destroying
the city! We have to get out!
[GIANT CUBE growls]
[LUCY whimpers]
This horrible sound!
[MARD GEER]
Demons of Tartaros.
[LUCY gasps]
I've used the Alegria.
The intruders' lives
have been snuffed out.
Our plans remain unchanged.
The Face's activation
is imminent.
[SOLDIERS cheer]
Long live the Underworld King!
[LUCY] No way, he can't have
really wiped out everyone else.
And I thought Wendy had already
stopped Face. Maybe he's lying.
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY]
This is gross! Ah!
[MARD GEER] However, I sense
that one unfortunate human soul
has managed to avoid
the Alegria's reach.
A timely vacancy has arisen
amongst the Nine Demon Gates.
Whoever slays this
human may fill it.
[SOLDIER A]
A vacancy?
[SOLDIER B]
That spot'll be mine!
And if a Demon Gate
should kill the human.
They shall receive an
even greater reward.
Good hunting.
[LUCY] Could it be true?
Am I the only one left?
No. Don't think like that.
Believe in your friends!
[SOLDIER A grunts]
It's the human!
[SOLDIER B]
I see her!
[SOLDIER C]
This one is mine!
[LUCY] Sorry boys,
but I've got other plans.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[SOLDIER D]
Three men down!
[SOLDIER E]
Let 'em swim!
[SOLDIER F]
Can't dodge forever!
[LUCY yells]
[SOLDIER D groans]
[SOLDIERS]
You're dead!
Open! Gate of the Archer!
Sagittarius!
[SAGITTARIUS winnies]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[gasps]
[LUMMY] Promotion time!
Promotion time!
I'm gonna be a Demon Gate!
Stop spinning
towards my lady!
She deflected every shot!
[LUMMY]
Projectiles are useless
against my demon curse
of slipperiness!
[LUMMY yells]
[SAGITTARIUS groans]
Take a break, Sagittarius!
[LUCY]
Open. Gate of the Maiden!
Virgo!
You want this bunny
girl punished, yes?
A skanky maid?!
The hell is this?!
You're totally copying me!
How so?
[LUCY screams]
Princess! There's
something else here!
[TORAFUZAR growls]
Open. Gate of the Lion, Leo!
[LUCY]
No!
You stopped my blade barehanded!
Impressive, not even Regulus'
power could block it all.
Thanks Loke! You okay?
[LOKE]
I'll be fine.
Ah! A hottie!
Now how exactly
am I copying you?
[LUMMY]
Sir Torafuzar?
Would you mind if I took
the credit for this kill?
I care not for glory.
I care only about my mission!
He's strong, but
I can handle him.
[panting]
[VIRGO] Keeping two gates open
at once, it looks painful.
[LOKE] Virgo and I use more
magic power than most.
For Lucy's sake.
[VIRGO]
For the sake of my princess.
[LOKE]
I'll fight fast!
[VIRGO]
I'll end this!
[ALL grunting]
[panting]
[JACKAL]
Oh, look! A human!
[JACKAL laughs]
More eye candy!
A third demon?
This is bad!
You lose!
[LOKE grunts]
Strange, I thought that there
was only one of you left.
Heh. Like it matters.
[LUCY] How is he here?
We already beat him!
He self-destructed!
[FRANMALTH] We possess
the power of immortality.
Our lab is the most
valuable tool in the world,
and as long as we have that,
we can keep coming back.
[LUCY] This guy gave
Natsu a hard time.
But it's not like I can summon
another celestial spirit.
It's up to me!
[JACKAL chuckles]
You haven't forgotten how
my curse works, have ya?
[LUCY whimpers]
[LUCY screams]
Lucy!
Princess!
Where are my friends?
And what's that red stuff
all over the walls?
[JACKAL]
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
[LUCY yelps]
[screams]
[JACKAL laughs]
[LUCY screams]
Stop playing. If you're going
to kill her, then do it.
The blue cat and the
fireball are dead.
Which means torturing
their little friend here
is the only kinda revenge
I'm prob'ly gonna get!
So I gotta savor the moment!
Oh, no!
[LOKE] Between keeping our gates
open and taking those attacks,
she's gotta be
close to her limit.
[LUCY]
Every time I've needed saving,
one of them has been there.
[LUCY] Now it's my turn.
I can't let them down!
Lucy!
[LUCY]
I don't care how strong you are!
You aren't drownin'
on me, are ya?
[LUCY] Now it's my turn.
I can't let them down!
[JACKAL]
Take this!
[LUCY yelps]
Lucy!
[LUCY]
I don't care how strong you are!
You won't beat me!
[LUCY]
Not until I've saved my friends.
What is she...? Princess,
no! It's too much!
Open. Gate of the Water Bearer!
Aquarius!
You're going to push
yourself too far!
You can't open
three gates at once!
[JACKAL growls]
[LUCY]
Please. Please come.
You're even stupider
than I thought.
She passed out!
Princess!
Glad you made it.
I'm going to say this one
more time. You're a damn idiot.
Who the hell is that?
She's my friend.
Just stay outta my way. [yells]
[JACKAL groaning]
[LUMMY screams]
This is too much for you!
You need to close
one of our gates
while you still
have the strength!
That thing.
It's swimming
against my current!
Water's a specialty of mine!
[AQUARIUS screams]
Leave Aquarius alone!
Damn it!
[VIRGO]
I'm on my way!
Not for long you aren't!
[LOKE]
What the...?
[LOKE screams]
[VIRGO screams]
Loke! Virgo! Ah!
[gasps]
Goodbye, princess.
[LOKE]
I'm Sorry. We failed.
[AQUARIUS whimpering]
[JACKAL]
So what?
Bringin' out three chumps
at once was your big play?
Looks like Fairy Tail's
last wizard standing
is all tuckered out.
[LUCY whimpers]
I can grant you a swift end.
Now where's the fun in that?
Here, here!
If we play our cards right,
we can torture her for hours!
But remember, we're gonna
give me all the credit!
[LUCY]
I can't let it end like this!
Everyone's counting on me!
[LUCY]
There has to be a way.
[LUCY groaning]
[laughs]
OMG, humans are
so lame! [laughs]
[LUCY whimpers]
[JACKAL laughs]
[TORAFUZAR]
I've had enough of your games.
If you won't finish her, I will.
[JACKAL] Huh? Tell me,
whose side are you on, here?
If it's death you're after,
I'd be happy to give ya one.
I'm through with this.
Suit yourself.
[laughs] Well, now that
I have permission.
[LUMMY]
So, what's next?
I'd like to direct your
attention to her boobs.
They're way too big.
Let's blow 'em up! [laughs]
[JACKAL laughs]
Ka... boom! Ka... boom!
Ka... boom?
Noisy twerp. [laughs]
You blew up... your comrade?
Why, yes I did. And if that's
how I treat my friends,
then think what's
in store for you.
This is gonna be fun. [laughs]
[JACKAL grunts]
The hell?!
[JACKAL gasps]
That you, Aquarius?
This lousy water! Ah!
Listen up. I can't beat them,
I can only slow 'em down.
Same goes for the
rest of the zodiac.
These demons are too strong.
[LUCY]
Yeah.
[AQUARIUS] But there's still
one way that you can win this.
[LUCY]
There is?
[AQUARIUS] We barely have the
time for me to say this once,
so pay attention.
You're strong, Lucy.
Strong enough to keep
three gates open.
And strong enough to summon him.
[AQUARIUS]
The Celestial Spirit King.
Is that possible?
Why else would I say it?
This won't be easy,
but it's our only chance.
His Strike from the Stars
can obliterate any foe.
Even this one.
Call him. But how?
I don't have his gate key.
[AQUARIUS] The Celestial
Spirit King has no key, Lucy.
There's another way to open
his gate. With a Zodiac key.
The price is a
hefty one though.
You can open the Gate
of the King only once.
And only by breaking
a golden key.
Forever.
[LUCY gasps] But that would
mean losing one of my spirits.
[JACKAL]
I'm gonna make you pay
for every second of my
time you've waste-- Ah!
[AQUARIUS] You can't just break
any golden key, either.
The king's gate will only
open if the level of trust
between wizard and spirit
is especially strong.
[LUCY] There has to be another
way. I won't do that.
I mean it!
It's like you're telling me to
pick a best friend to betray!
[AQUARIUS] It's not a
betrayal if I let you.
Only thing I've ever trusted
you to do is act like a fool,
but we do go way back.
So I think it'll work.
Are you saying I should...?
[AQUARIUS] Do what it takes
to save your friends? Yes.
[LUCY]
But you're one of them!
I'm not about to sacrifice
one friend to save another.
It's wrong!
There's another way.
There has to be!
All we need to do
is figure it out!
Do you think I
would suggest this
if there was still
another option?
This is the only
chance that you have.
No! That's not true!
[JACKAL growls]
You hear that?
He'll break through soon.
You have to be strong. Please!
[LUCY]
I can't!
[AQUARIUS] It's not like
you breaking my key
will kill me, okay?
I'll be fine.
It'll be like I moved.
Somewhere very far away.
That would still be too sad.
Maybe for you, but
I'll be relieved.
[JACKAL growling]
[AQUARIUS] Your mother was
an extraordinary person.
The best master I've ever had.
When she lost her life and
my key was passed on to you,
I could barely take it.
You were an ignorant brat
who cried all the time
and took everything
for granted.
You didn't inherit an ounce of
your mother's natural grace.
But, I had to tolerate you
because you were
Layla's daughter.
[AQUARIUS] I loathed you.
Despised you.
For such a very long time.
I don't care if you hate me!
You were still my first
friend and I love you!
There's nothing you can
say that will change that!
Stop trying!
[AQUARIUS]
Quit acting like a damn child!
You can lose every friend you
have, or you can just lose me!
[LUCY cries]
[AQUARIUS] What matters
most in life? Keys?
Memories?
Your guilty conscience?
Or is it this? The strength
to make sacrifices
to protect the ones you love,
even when it hurts you.
If that's it then break
my key right now!
Natsu isn't coming!
It's all on you!
[JACKAL laughs] Pick your
words carefully, girls.
This'll be the last
fight you ever have!
[LUCY] I love you Aquarius.
I love you so much.
Yeah, I know! Now do it!
[LUCY yells]
[AQUARIUS]
Feels like my heart's on fire.
[LUCY yells]
[AQUARIUS]
I meant what I said.
I hate this stupid brat.
[LUCY]
Open!
Mermaid! Mermaid!
[AQUARIUS]
I can't stand her, but...
[LUCY]
Gate of the...
[AQUARIUS]
These emotions.
[LUCY] it can't be a crime
to protect the people
you care about!
Sound wicked awesome!
Oh, my hunk!
Little Lucy thinks she
can seduce a man?
Good luck with that scrawny bod.
For you to make me laugh.
Uh...
[AQUARIUS] These damned
feelings. I can't stop them.
[LUCY laughs]
Aw, come on! Bath time
is a lot of fun isn't it?
It's no so much fun that
you gotta call me
every time you get in the tub!
Whoops! I'm sorry!
[AQUARIUS] This better be
the last time I tell you this.
But don't ever dream
of summoning me
from your stupid little
pet prison again!
It's a goldfish bowl
for crying out loud!
[LUCY] But he's got
a tail, just like you!
Are you sayin' me and that
simple little creature
have something in common?
Because that is insulting!
I didn't mean to make you mad.
[AQUARIUS]
Uh! Sheesh.
You seriously need to find some
other rugrats to play with.
There aren't any.
That's why I'm so lonely.
[AQUARIUS grunts]
You make me happy. But I
always seem to make you mad.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, well. You're not
lonely anymore.
[LUCY]
Yeah. You're right.
I'm definitely not.
[AQUARIUS] Despite myself,
I'm gonna miss you.
You suck. I'm gonna
miss you bad.
[LUCY]
Open! Gate of the King!
[AQUARIUS] I'm grateful though
for every moment we shared.
Where'd the water go?
[KING growls]
[SOLDIERS murmur]
What was that?
Plutogrim's been ruptured?
[SOLDIERS yell]
Ah! What did you do?
What are you?
[LUCY cries]
[LUCY]
Aquarius is gone.
But the Celestial Spirit King
has answered our call.
Mard Geer stands confident
atop the smoldering ruin
of what used to be
Tartaros' headquarters.
Unfazed by the great
titan before him.
The Kings of two worlds
are about to collide.
I don't have to time
to grieve for her.
But I can take strength
from her words.
And I will protect
the ones I love.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
Celestial Spirit King
vs. Underworld King"
This is the time to fight!