You hideous soul.
You demon!
Close, old man.
But the meaning of
the name "Spriggan"
is much more akin
to "hideous fairy."
--It's Gramps!
--He found him!
[ERZA, LUCY]
Master!
Hey, Gramps!
My children are here.
Guys. I saw Zeref!
He was with Zeref!
[gasps]
Are you sure?
[ZEREF]
Natsu, after all this time...
...you have come.
[NATSU]
Zeref is here?
Like, on this continent?
I can hardly believe it myself.
But this Empire's leader,
who they call Spriggan,
is actually the
Black Wizard Zeref.
[gasps]
How is that possible?
The emperor is Zeref?
[MAKAROV]
Since you've come all this way,
I assume Mest has filled
you in on the situation,
and what I was trying to
accomplish by traveling here.
He has.
[WENDY] I'm just so happy
that you're okay.
I've been far too naive
through this whole ordeal.
I came here believing that they
would be willing to negotiate,
but that was just a fantasy.
And before I made
the journey west,
I put the future of
the guild in jeopardy.
All that heartache and
pain was for nothing.
I've never felt such regret
and embarrassment in my life.
This year was tough, but we
all made our way through it.
And we're even stronger.
It really is true.
And the bond we share
could never be broken.
That's how we found
each other again.
[ERZA] If concern for another
is what pushes you to act,
then it means something.
Showing you care is important.
Master, you taught
us that lesson.
[NATSU] Come on, Gramps.
Let's go home.
Fairy Tail's waiting.
[MAKAROV]
I'm ready.
[CARLA] Well, we've a
lot of catching up to do,
but first, we should
get out of this place.
Yeah, you're right.
[MAKAROV]
Do I know this person?
[MEST] I used too many
Direct Lines in a row,
so I'm running low
on magic power.
I only have enough to
teleport us one more time.
I think it would be best
to use that last teleport
to reach Sorano's ship.
So we'll need to travel a bit on
land, until we're within range.
[AJEEL] Makarov, are you
really leaving so soon?
And after we were getting
to know each other.
I have a farewell gift for you.
I'd like you to have it
before you take a long
nap in the ground.
[chuckles]
No! Ajeel!
Impossible! How did he find us?
[AJEEL]
Sand.
Sand is nice. It tells me
almost everything.
[GRAY] This guy's got
as much magic power
as the girl on Caracol Island.
[chuckles]
Very nice.
[MAKAROV]
Stop!
You mustn't fight him.
He's much too powerful!
We should run!
[gasps]
For real?
Our master clearly gave
the order to retreat!
But, Erza!
[ERZA]
Let's go, now!
We already have a magic-mobile
ready and waiting!
[yells]
[AJEEL]
Huh?
[GRAY]
Come on, get in!
[NATSU]
Ugh. Can't we walk?
[ERZA] I'll drive us!
SE plug, connected!
Here it goes!
So those are Makarov's lackeys.
Huh. This'll be fun.
This sucks.
Sure does.
Can we go faster?
I'm trying!
He's coming!
What is that thing?
[GRAY]
Whoa! It's a giant sand monster!
Not good!
[GRAY]
It's gaining on us!
You and I need to try
and stop it, Lucy!
Right!
So sick.
[LUCY]
Sorry for squishing you, Natsu!
No, don't! He's too
powerful for us to fight!
Yeah, well, I'm not sure
about that, Gramps!
[LUCY]
Star Dress.
Sagittarius Form!
There's so much magic power
coming from those two!
They told me they'd
gotten stronger,
but to have grown so much
in only a year is incredible!
[GRAY]
Let's show 'em what we got.
[AJEEL] So you're actually
gonna put up a fight, are ya?
Ice Make Silver.
[AJEEL gasps]
Looks like Gray froze
everything with that attack!
Impressive!
Nice!
Now those sand creatures
are comin' for us!
I'll take care of them!
Star Shot!
This is even more fun
than I thought it would be!
He's gone!
Beneath us!
He merged with the sand;
watch for an attack!
[CARLA]
Huh?
[AJEEL]
Antlion Pit!
[gasps] What's happening?
Damn it!
[AJEEL]
Heh. Man, that was pathetic!
You guys shoulda stayed
back in Ishgar
'cause you're really in
over your heads here.
[ERZA]
Everyone, out of the car! Hurry!
[WENDY coughs]
Oh, no! We've lost
the magic-mobile!
[CARLA]
Happy! Please! Hang on!
[HAPPY] I just swallowed
a mouthful of sand!
The hell?
It's actually pulling us down!
I can't move my legs anymore!
[GROUP grunting]
[AJEEL] I can't count how many
people I've killed with this.
Entire cities have been
swallowed up whole inside it.
[growls]
My Antlion Trap is like
a gateway to hell.
Nobody has ever escaped from it.
Heh.
Before you go to your graves
thinking that you're
something special,
you should know this!
You're just a bunch of losers
like all of the other wizards
we've killed over the years!
We're on a different
level altogether
than you maggots from Ishgar!
The gods have abandoned your
whole freakin' continent!
It'll be so easy for
Alvarez to take it over!
Sucks to be you guys!
[AJEEL laughing]
[AJEEL] Oh, man! The looks on
your faces are priceless!
[gasps]
[NATSU] So the gods
abandoned Ishgar, huh?
That's not a problem!
Because Fairy Tail is
still watching over it.
He made my sand evaporate?
[NATSU yells]
[gasps]
Nice shot!
It's been forever since somebody
got in a solid punch like that!
Yeah! Bring it on!
Cool it down!
All dried up.
[NATSU]
What's he doing?!
Not this again!
It's like it's alive!
It's so strong. What do we do?
You won't hurt my children!
[AJEEL]
Whoa!
[ALL yell]
As long as I draw breath, I'll
protect my family at any cost!
[AJEEL]
Hm.
Come on, Gramps, let us go
so we can pummel this guy!
Natsu, would you
please stop yelling?
Is that so?
Well, you won't be drawing
breath for that much longer.
If you think you
can protect them,
you don't understand the power
of the Spriggan Twelve.
[MAKAROV]
Huh?
You'll die together.
Drowning in my sands of death!
[gasps]
Now, Mest! Teleport us!
Where can we go?
[NATSU]
Gramps!
[MAKAROV] I will keep you safe,
if it's the last thing I do!
I swear on my life!
Here it comes!
And every single thing
that gets caught
in the path of this sandstorm
shrivels up and dies instantly!
[NATSU]
Gramps, no!
[ERZA]
Master!
[GRAY]
Run!
[LUCY]
Get outta here!
[AJEEL] You're gonna be
a bunch of Fairy mummies
in just a second.
[gasps]
[MAKAROV]
Laxus?
Is that really him?
That sandstorm was completely
obliterated with only one shot!
He's always been
flashy like that.
It's amazing!
Sounds like him!
Hey, old man. You're even older.
We're behind enemy lines,
so we gotta get outta here ASAP.
Thank this guy for the ship!
Gajeel?
I can smell Levy and
Lily up there too.
Hold on just a second!
How are you and Laxus not
puking your guts out?
[JUVIA]
Gray, my darling!
Don't worry, I'm here too!
[ELFMAN] Hey, I wanna
say somethin' manly!
[LISANNA]
How is that gonna help?
[MIRAJANE] This ship's been
modified so Dragon Slayers
can ride on it and not get sick!
[MAKAROV]
Hmm.
Hey, Wendy!
You've really grown up
since last time we met.
She's gone from little
girl to little lady.
Seems like everybody's
changed from last year.
Oh, yeah?
I don't think I've changed
all that much, actually.
You're down there,
too, right, Mest?
Teleport onto the ship
if you're able!
Comin' up!
[AJEEL]
You can't run from me!
[LAXUS]
No one's running.
We're just flying
back home, okay?
And I'm gonna get cranky
if we miss dinner.
[AJEEL grunts]
[AJEEL]
That was intense.
They must be taking
this seriously.
Hm?
I guess you put up that barrier
as some kind of favor to me?
[AUGUST] Even an old man
like me finds it painful
to lose a comrade in battle.
So you think that little
light show woulda killed me?
Sorry, August, you must
be getting senile.
It begins, Natsu. Game on.
[ALL groaning]
What do you think about
our manly rescue?
You're safe now!
The mission to get
Master back is a success!
Gotta say, I'm surprised
to see ya here.
We knew the master
was in trouble,
so we came up with
a rescue plan.
Luckily, we got
Laxus to help out!
You got some nerve
leavin' without us!
Well, it was a covert operation.
Bein' on a ship is awesome
when you don't need to
hurl the whole time!
Whaddaya say you and
me fight to celebrate?
I'll pass.
My children.
It feels so good to be with
my Fairy Tail family again!
[LUCY]
Let's have a toast!
Fairy Tail is back in business!
[FAIRY TAIL]
Cheers!
[MEMBER G]
Welcome back, Master!
Hang on, if Erza's
our master now,
then what in the heck are
we supposed to call him?
Mr. Makarov, I suppose?
I don't know; doesn't
feel quite right to me.
[FRIED sighs]
Call him "Master."
Because I'll be stepping down.
Oh, sweet Little Asca!
I missed you!
[MEMBER H]
I'm confused.
Does this make him
our eighth master?
[MEMBER I] Can't believe
this is his third time!
I mean, how does he keep
getting revived like that?
[MEMBER J]
Uhh, it's not like he died.
Looks like I'll be guild master
till I die this time around.
Now that's a man's dedication!
I believe that's what you said
the last time this happened.
[LISANNA laughs]
All right, let's
crack open the booze
and get this shindig started!
[MEMBERS]
It's time to party!
[GRAY] I'm kinda surprised
you guys decided
to join Blue Pegasus.
There are worse jobs
than serving customers.
Yeah, but I feel way more at
home in a rowdy bar like this.
I do have to ask how Laxus
fit in at that guild.
I mean, did he actually do the
"hospitality" part of the job?
He did once in a while.
I can't say it was
very hospitable.
What happens at the guild
hall stays in the guild hall.
Did you manage to get
in contact with Sorano
after we left that place?
Yeah, I did. And she
was not a happy camper.
Then we teleported into
an underwater temple.
And everywhere you looked,
it was completely surrounded
by so many different kinds
of beautifully yummy fishies!
I heard the news.
You're the most recent member
of the motion sickness club?
Yeah.
Aw, don't let it get
you down, Wendy.
I've always been that way!
[GRAY]
I don't see how that's
supposed to make
her feel any better.
[GAJEEL]
You lookin' for a fight?
[NATSU]
Bring it on!
[CANA] How did that little
exchange turn into a fight?
[WENDY] I'll never ride
in a carriage again.
[CARLA] If it's that
big of a deal for you.
[JUVIA]
Oh, Gray! Please!
I wanna know what your
"hospitality" is like!
[GRAY]
What the hell do you mean?
[CANA]
Man, did I miss you guys!
[ERZA] Can you believe we can't
get Star Mangos in Fiore?
[MIRAJANE]
I've never even heard of 'em.
[ELFMAN]
Hmph. Do they taste manly?
[LISANNA]
That sounds disgusting!
The guild hall's just as
noisy as I remember it!
If you ask me,
it sounds like things
are finally gettin'
back to normal!
[LUCY] We were able to
get our beloved master
back to Fairy Tail.
And Laxus and the
Thunder Legion, to boot.
But during our journey,
we found out that the Alvarez
Empire on the western continent
has wizards more powerful
than any we've faced before.
But what's even scarier is
that the Black Wizard Zeref
rules over that empire.
Although there, he's known
as "Emperor Spriggan."
And not only that, he's
planning on coming to Ishgar
to take the Lumen Histoire.
Our guild's biggest treasure.
The crystal that contains
the body of our first master.
There's gonna be a war for sure.
And I'm positive it's gonna be
the most grueling battle
we've been through.
I don't even wanna think
about losing anyone.
There has to be a way we can
get through this in one piece.
I just want the feeling we
share here to last forever.
To live inside this moment...
that's my deepest wish.
[ALL]
Huh?
Children. Let me apologize.
I'm not going to make
any excuses for myself.
I took your home and your
way of life away from you.
That was a mistake on my part.
Don't worry,
Mest explained it all!
You followed the only
course of action
you believed you had
to protect us.
We understand your feelings.
And anyway, the guild's
back together now,
so everything's fine!
That's why I say we should
have a little more booze
and a little less boo-hoos.
[MAKAROV]
This is serious.
Because I wasn't able to
negotiate for our safety,
there's no doubt
Alvarez will invade.
[FAIRY TAIL gasps]
[MAKAROV]
They are a true superpower,
and they will throw
everything they have at us.
So what?! I'm ready!
[NATSU] Time and time again,
we've put everything on the line
for the sake of the guild!
No matter how tough
our enemies may be,
we fight for what's
most important to us.
That's what makes us so strong!
It's not that I'm not scared,
but no matter how I feel,
I can't let go of
my responsibility.
Plus, I know I can count
on everybody else.
What I'm most afraid of...
...is losing what we
all have together.
[NATSU]
So we can't run away from this.
We have to fight!
For our family, and for
the bond we share.
We gotta make a stand!
And it's not just about winning!
This time, our fight
is about living!
[ALL chuckle]
I think everyone's made up
their minds, old man.
[MAKAROV grunts]
[MAKAROV]
As have I.
Listen up!
We are going to make
them rue the day
they chose to mess
with our family!
Let's take them down!
[FAIRY TAIL]
Yeah!
I'm all fired up now!
We're gonna have to give
it everything we've got!
Well, don't we always?
This foe's like none
we've ever faced.
We'll be fighting Zeref.
I'm gonna find E.N.D.
We'll make it through this
fight just like all the others.
...get my claws into those big
magic meanies from Alvarez.
I'll protect the guild
this time. I swear I will.
Like a real man!
After training for
the last year,
I'm ready to show off the
new skills I picked up!
Whoa, you've actually been
training for this entire year?
[LISANNA] Oh, yeah, she's
like way stronger now.
And I am too!
Oh, man, did I miss this
frickin' guild, or what?
[LAXUS]
Heh.
Before we get too carried away,
there's some extremely
important information
I must share with you.
It's concerning
the Lumen Histoire.
Or rather, what's
formally referred to
as the "Fairy Heart."
[MAVIS] I think perhaps
I should be the one
to explain this to them, Sixth--
or, excuse me--Eighth Master.
[MAKAROV]
First Master?
[FAIRY TAIL gasping, chattering]
[ERZA]
Is this a projection of her?
Or is she really here?
It's likely... you've not
heard of Fairy Heart.
For many years,
it's been our guild's
most closely guarded secret.
For good reason.
Because the world must never
learn exactly what it holds.
However, I believe it's
crucial that you know
why Zeref would go to
such lengths to get it.
And also... about my own sin.
You're sure?
[MAVIS]
I am.
It's time for my long-held
secrets to be revealed.
[MAVIS] This is a tale
of a boy and girl,
of the awful curse they shared,
and the primordial magic...
that they sought together.
[LUCY gasps]
[MAVIS]
Over 100 years ago,
a girl living in a world
full of turmoil and strife
crossed paths with someone who
would change her life forever:
A young black wizard.
The gears of fate
turn constantly;
at times, offering chance
glimpses of hope,
but also producing
heart-breaking contradiction.
Next Time: "Mavis and Zeref."
This is a tale of the
primordial essence of magic.