- HEY GUYS! READY FOR
SOME MORE FAIRY TAIL?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS
ON IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO
CLOSE TO THE TV!
- PREVIOUSLY ON FAIRY TAIL!
WE WERE ABLE TO STOP
PHANTOM'S MAGIC GIANT
FROM CASTING THE
ABYSS BREAK SPELL
BUT OUR GUILD HALL
WAS DESTROYED!
ERZA IS BUSY FIGHTING
PHANTOM'S MASTER,
WHO'S REALLY CREEPY
AND REALLY STRONG.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE NATSU
IS ABOUT TO FINISH OFF GAJEEL,
THE IRON DRAGON SLAYER.
AT LEAST I HOPE SO!
- ( theme song playing )
- THOSE SHADES AIN'T
SLOWIN DOWN!
- SO BE IT. THEY MAY HAVE
DESTROYED OUR GUILD HALL
BUT THIS FIGHT
AIN'T OVER YET!
- YEAH!
- Happy: FAIRY LAW!
- I'M GONNA MAKE YOU PAY FOR
WHAT YOU DID TO MY FRIENDS.
MESSIN' WITH FAIRY TAIL
IS THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
YOU'VE EVER MADE.
- THE ONLY MISTAKE I MADE
WAS NOT KILLIN' YOU SOONER!
IRON DRAGON HARD FIST!
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
I'M THE STRONGEST!
- YOU'RE THROUGH, BLACK STEEL!
FLAME LOTUS FIRE DRAGON FIST!
LEVY! JET! DROY! NAB!
MACAO! GRAMPS! ERZA!
AND LUCY!
THIS IS FOR ATTACKING THEM AND
DESTROYING OUR GUILD HALL!
- AL! YOU SEE THAT LIGHT?
- IT'S NATSU!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENIN'!
- GAJEEL'S NEVER LOST A FIGHT!
- Lucy: WHERE IS HE?
- NATSU?
- NATSU! HEY!
- ALRIGHT! IT LOOKS LIKE HE WON!
- YOU CAN'T DEFEAT ME.
- OH YEAH? I THINK I JUST DID.
- HE'S DOWN!
- WELL, THAT WAS FUN, BUT I
THINK I'M GONNA REST A BIT.
- WHAT A MESS. AW, MAN.
TALK ABOUT OVERDOIN' IT.
- AYE! THAT'S NATSU FOR YA!
- DESTRUCTIVE AS ALWAYS.
BUT IT'S STILL PRETTY COOL.
- THAT GUY'S INSANE. HE TORE
THE WHOLE PLACE DOWN!
MAN, I HAD NO IDEA
THAT FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS
COULD BE SO POWERFUL!
- YEAH, THEY'RE AWESOME.
UH, NEVERMIND.
- MY, WHAT AN UNRULY
DRAGON YOU HAVE.
- HE MAY BE UNRULY
BUT HE'S ALSO AN EXTREMELY
POWERFUL WIZARD.
IN FACT, I'D SAY THAT HE'S
JUST AS STRONG AS I AM
IF NOT STRONGER.
- HEH. THERE'S NO NEED TO
BE SO MODEST, TITANIA ERZA.
YOUR MAGIC IS JUST AS
SPECTACULAR AS SALAMANDER'S.
YOU'RE THE FIRST WIZARD WHO'S
EVER BEEN ABLE TO LAST THIS LONG
AGAINST ME IN BATTLE.
TRUTH BE TOLD, WE'D BE MORE
EQUALLY MATCHED IN POWER
IF YOU HADN'T TAKEN A DIRECT HIT
FROM THE JUPITER CANNON
EARLIER TODAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT REALLY IRKS ME
ABOUT FAIRY TAIL?
THE FACT THAT THERE ARE SO MANY
POWERFUL WIZARDS LIKE YOURSELF
WHO ARE ALIGNED
WITH MAKAROV.
SINCE YOU CAN'T BE
TEMPTED TO JOIN PHANTOM
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO CHANGE THAT--
KILL YOU!
THAT'LL SEND THE OLD
COOT INTO A DEEP DESPAIR.
IMAGINE HOW HE'LL FEEL
WHEN HE AWAKENS TO FIND HIS
DEAR GUILD HALL DESTROYED
AND HIS "CHILDREN"
DEAD AND GONE.
HE'D BE LOST; COMPLETELY
CONSUMED BY SORROW.
ONCE HE'S BEEN REDUCED
TO THAT MISERABLE STATE,
I CAN SWOOP IN AND KILL HIM,
BUT FIRST I'LL MAKE HIM SUFFER.
I'LL TORTURE HIM UNTIL HE HAS NO
CHOICE BUT TO WITHER AND DIE!
AS LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER,
PHANTOM LORD HAS
ALWAYS BEEN AT THE TOP.
WE HAVE THE MOST
POWERFUL WIZARDS
WITH THE STRONGEST SPELLS;
WE ALSO HAVE MORE CAPITAL
AND MORE MEMBERS
THAN ANY OTHER GUILD.
HOWEVER, RECENTLY FAIRY
TAIL HAS BEGUN TO CATCH UP
AND OUR POSITION AS
LEADER IS IN JEOPARDY.
THE NAMES ERZA, LAXUS, AND
MYSTOGAN BECAME WIDELY KNOWN,
AND STORIES OF SALAMANDER SPREAD
ACROSS THE LAND LIKE WILDFIRE.
NOW PHANTOM LORD AND FAIRY
TAIL ARE CONSIDERED EQUALS!
THE TOP TWO GUILDS
REPRESENTING THIS KINGDOM.
THE THOUGHT DISGUSTS ME.
I REFUSE TO BE EQUATED
TO SUCH A FEEBLE GUILD!
- Erza: SILENCE!
SO, WE'RE FIGHTING
FOR OUR LIVES,
JUST BECAUSE YOU'VE HAD
A FIT OF JEALOUSY?
- JEALOUSY? THAT'S ABSURD!
WE SIMPLY WANTED TO
PROVE TO THE KINGDOM
THAT WE ARE
THE DOMINANT GUILD.
- HOW COULD YOU? AND FOR
SUCH A PETTY REASON?
- WHILE I'VE NEVER BEEN
PARTICULARLY FOND OF YOUR GUILD,
MY DISTASTE FOR YOU WAS NOT
WHAT TRIGGERED THIS WAR.
WE WERE HIRED BY THE PATRIARCH
OF THE HEARTFILIA FAMILY
TO FIND HIS MISSING DAUGHTER.
- Erza: LUCY.
- THE CHILD OF ONE OF THE
KINGDOM'S WEALTHIEST MEN
IS NOW IN FAIRY TAIL.
SO MAKAROV'S TRYING TO BUY
HIS WAY TO THE TOP, ISN'T HE?
NOW THAT YOUR GUILD
HAS UNFETTERED ACCESS
TO THE HEARTFILIA
FAMILY FORTUNE,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF
TIME BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
THAT IS, IF WE DON'T
COMPLETELY WIPE YOU OUT FIRST.
- IT'S LAUGHABLE HOW
CONCERNED YOU ARE
ABOUT SOMETHING AS SILLY
AS YOUR GUILD'S RANKING.
BUT, I'M EVEN MORE AMUSED
BY HOW INCREDIBLY MISINFORMED
YOU ARE ABOUT LUCY.
- WHAT?
- SHE CAME TO US AS A RUNAWAY!
SHE DOESN'T HAVE ACCESS
TO HER FAMILY'S FORTUNE!
Erza: SHE RENTS A PLACE FOR
70,000 JEWEL A MONTH!
SHE WORKS HARD TO MAKE A LIVING.
SHE FIGHTS ALONGSIDE US.
SHE LAUGHS WITH US AND
SHE CRIES WITH US.
SHE'S NO DIFFERENT THAN ANY
OTHER MEMBER OF OUR GUILD!
- I WANNA STAY WITH YOU GUYS
'CAUSE I LOVE BEIN'
IN FAIRY TAIL!
- AND SHE'S WHY WE'RE AT WAR?
WE WOULD NEVER
BETRAY HER LIKE THAT!
YOU'D HAVE TO KILL US FIRST!
SHE MAY BE THE DAUGHTER
OF THE HEARTFILIA FAMILY,
BUT JUST AS FLOWERS DON'T GET
TO CHOOSE WHERE THEY BLOOM,
CHILDREN DON'T GET TO
CHOOSE THEIR PARENTS!
( Lucy sobs )
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT LUCY
OR THE TEARS THAT SHE HAS SHED!
- WELL, I'LL FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH!
I'M NOT GOING TO HAND HER
OVER TO HER FATHER
WITHOUT REAPING A
BENEFIT OF SOME SORT.
I'LL MAKE HER MY PRISONER UNTIL
HER FATHER MEETS MY DEMANDS.
I'M GOING TO BLEED THE
HEARTFILIA FAMILY
OF THEIR FORTUNE
AND THEIR PRECIOUS
MONEY-MAKING BUSINESSES!
- CURSE YOU!
- I WOULDN'T KEEP STRUGGLING
LIKE THAT IF I WERE YOU.
IT'S GOING TO MAKE
THIS MORE PAINFUL!
( Erza screams )
YOU'RE NOT FEELING VERY
WELL, ARE YOU DEAR?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BUCK UP
BECAUSE IT'S ALMOST TIME.
I WANT YOU TO MAKE AN
APPEARANCE BEFORE YOUR PEERS.
ONCE THEY SEE THEIR BELOVED
ERZA IN SUCH A PITIFUL STATE,
THEY'RE SURE TO SURRENDER TO US!
- YOU'RE A DESPICABLE MAN!
- NOW, NOW, INSULTING
ME LIKE THAT
ISN'T GOING TO HELP
YOUR SITUATION.
(sinister laugh)
- I'D RATHER DIE THAN CAUSE MY
GUILD MATES TO SURRENDER.
I LEAVE THE REST
UP TO YOU, NATSU.
( thunder rumbles )
BUT HOW?
- YOU HAVE SHED THE
BLOOD OF OUR CHILDREN.
AND THAT IS UNFORGIVABLE.
THEY HAVE BEEN MADE TO SUFFER
BECAUSE OF THE INCOMPETENCE
OF THEIR PARENTS.
WE ARE BOTH TO BLAME, JOSE.
THIS WAR BETWEEN US
HAS GONE ON LONG ENOUGH.
LET'S END THIS HERE AND NOW!
- Erza: MASTER!
- IF WE FIGHT IT COULD
CREATE A CATASTROPHE.
- IN ORDER TO SAVE MY GUILD,
I WILL GLADLY TAKE THAT RISK!
( he laughs )
- I CAN FEEL THEIR FEAR;
THE TREES, THE EARTH, THE AIR.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY--
I HATE HUMANS!
THEY'RE SO DIM-WITTED THEY HAVE
NO IDEA HOW TO SOLVE A PROBLEM
WITHOUT RAISING THEIR FISTS!
YOU'RE A NIT-WIT, MAKAROV!
I TRIED TO WARN YOU, BUT OF
COURSE YOU NEVER LISTEN TO ME!
MYSTOGAN.
- MIND IF I HAVE THIS?
- HA, I WONDERED
HOW THE OLD GEEZER
WAS ABLE TO RECOVER SO QUICKLY.
NOW IT ALL MAKES SENSE.
WHEN MAKAROV WAS HIT
WITH THE DRAIN SPELL
YOU GATHERED HIS LOST MAGIC.
- I NEVER SAID
YOU COULD EAT THAT!
- THIS WAR WILL BE OVER SOON.
- I'M NOT A PROPONENT OF
ANY SORT OF VIOLENCE,
EVEN BETWEEN LOATHSOME HUMANS.
THAT BEING SAID, AREN'T
YOU ONE OF MAKAROV'S MEN?
DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME HERE.
YOUR ALLIES NEED YOUR HELP.
PHANTOM'S FLAGS.
THERE'S SO MANY.
HE MUST'VE OVERTHROWN
EVERY SINGLE ONE
OF THEIR BRANCHES
IN THE KINGDOM.
- MAY I TAKE ANOTHER
APPLE FOR THE ROAD?
- YOU ARE GOING TO
PICK UP THIS MESS
YOU MADE BEFORE YOU GO, RIGHT?
HONESTLY. I'LL NEVER
UNDERSTAND HUMANS.
THEY THIRST FOR POWER
AND FIND THEMSELVES AT WAR.
THEY FORGET HOW MUCH PAIN
AND SORROW IT CAN BRING.
ALL THAT MATTERS
IS THEIR VICTORY.
- I BELIEVE THERE IS A
WAY TO SAVE THEM
FROM THAT PAIN AND SORROW.
IT'S A SACRED LIGHT,
WHICH GUIDES US ALL.
- WHAT THE--? FOR
SOME STRANGE REASON
THIS WARM LIGHT REMINDS
ME OF THE MASTER.
- YOU KIDS NEED TO GET
OUT WHILE YOU CAN!
- GRAMPS!
- WE'LL STAY WITH YOU!
- NO, WE HAVE TO DO AS HE SAYS!
LET'S GO!
- BUT ERZA!
- SIS, YOU THINK YOU CAN STAND?
- WELL, WELL, NOW
THAT YOU'RE HERE,
I'VE NO INTEREST IN THOSE
"CHILDREN" OF YOURS.
I'LL EXTERMINATE THOSE PESTS
AFTER I'VE FINISHED YOU OFF.
- IF WE STAY HERE WE'RE ONLY
GOING TO GET IN HIS WAY.
HE CAN HANDLE THIS,
I HAVE FAITH.
- IT'S BEEN SIX YEARS SINCE
WE LAST CAME FACE TO FACE.
THEN, PHANTOM WAS NUMBER ONE
AND NO ONE KNEW HOW LARGE
YOUR FAIRY TAIL WOULD BECOME.
- BUT NOW IT'S BEEN
REDUCED TO RUBBLE.
- OUR GUILD HALL MAY
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED
BUT WE'RE STRONG AS EVER!
- I MUST ADMIT I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO THIS.
ALTHOUGH IT'S FROWNED UPON
BY THE COUNCIL--
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHO'S
THE SUPERIOR WIZARD SAINT.
- I COULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS
WITHOUT YOU, MY CHILDREN.
BLESS YOU ALL.
BE PROUD THAT YOU
ARE MEMBERS OF FAIRY TAIL!
- WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
- THE SKY.
- WATCH OUT!
- WE'RE SHAKIN'!
- WHAT THE--?
- IT'S AN EARTHQUAKE!
- DEAD WAVE!
- NATSU!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- OH YEAH.
- WHAT THE HECK IS
GOIN' ON IN THERE?
- PRETTY SURE THAT'S GRAMPS
IN THERE SETTLING THE SCORE.
- I'M IMPRESSED. YOU'VE SO MUCH
POWER AT YOUR COMMAND.
I CAN SEE WHY THE
COUNCIL NAMED YOU
ONE OF THE TEN WIZARD SAINTS.
HOWEVER, YOU'RE
MISUSING THAT POWER
FOR YOUR OWN PERSONAL GAIN.
YOU COULD'VE
BECOME A ROLE MODEL
FOR THE YOUNGER GENERATION.
INSTEAD YOU'VE BECOME A
LESSON IN WHAT NOT TO DO.
- WHAT IS THIS? A LECTURE?
- I'VE A RULE THAT SEEMS TO WORK
WELL WITH MY FAIRY TAIL KIDS.
I'LL GIVE YOU TO THE COUNT OF
THREE TO DO EXACTLY AS I SAY.
KNEEL TO ME.
- WHAT?
- ONE!
- SO YOU WANT ME TO CONCEDE
AND KNEEL BEFORE YOU?
NO WAY IN HELL!
- TWO!
- WHY WOULD THE MASTER
OF THE TOP GUILD
IN THIS KINGDOM
EVER STOOP SO LOW
AS TO KNEEL BEFORE YOU?
TECHNICALLY WE ARE
EQUALLY POWERFUL
BUT MY ABILITY TO BE HEARTLESS
MAKES ME EVEN STRONGER!
- THREE!
- YOU ARE THE ONE WHO SHOULD
BE KNEELING BEFORE ME!
NOW, YOU AND YOUR PRECIOUS
FAIRY TAIL "CHILDREN"
ARE GOING TO DIE!
- TIME'S UP!
- THIS IS IT!
- I INVOKE FAIRY LAW!
- WHERE'S THAT LIGHT
COMIN' FROM?
- IT'S SO BRIGHT!
- THEY'RE DISAPPEARING!
- WHAT'S HAPPENIN'?
- I THINK THE LIGHT'S KILLIN'
'EM. BUT WE'RE ALL STILL OKAY!
- YOU'RE RIGHT. IT MUST BE
SOMEBODY ON OUR SIDE.
- THIS IS FAIRY LAW.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- A SPELL THAT VANQUISHES
DARKNESS WITH SACRED LIGHT.
IT ONLY AFFECTS THOSE WHO
THE CASTER SEES AS THEIR ENEMY.
INCREDIBLE, ISN'T IT?
IT'S ONE OF THE MOST LEGENDARY
SPELLS IN EXISTENCE.
- YOU WILL NEVER BOTHER FAIRY
TAIL AGAIN, UNDERSTAND?
I'M SURE THE MAGIC COUNCIL
WILL BE WATCHING US
AFTER ALL THE CHAOS
WE'VE CAUSED.
YOU'D BETTER BE ON YOUR
BEST BEHAVIOR FROM NOW ON.
I KNOW I WILL.
- OUR MASTER HAS
FALLEN. HOW SAD.
THE OLD MAN'S LEFT HIMSELF
OPEN AGAIN. THIS IS MY CHANCE!
- THE WAR IS OVER. THERE'S NO
REASON FOR US TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
BUT IF YOU PUSH ME TO
THE POINT OF ANGER,
I'LL WIPE OUT YOUR ENTIRE
GUILD WITHOUT HESITATION!
NOW YOU KIDS GET OUTTA
HERE AND TAKE JOSE!
- ALRIGHT! WE BEAT PHANTOM!
- YEE-HAW!
- WE ARE VICTORIOUS!
BUT I HAD VERY LITTLE
TO DO WITH IT.
THIS VICTORY IS YOURS,
MY CHILDREN!
WE COULDN'T HAVE DONE
IT WITHOUT YOU, BIG GUY!
( singing in Japanese )
- POOR LUCY, SHE MUST'VE
BEEN REALLY SCARED
BACK WHEN JOSE
KIDNAPPED HER, HUH?
- TELL ME ABOUT IT! DID YA
SEE HOW HE LOOKED AT HER?
IT WAS SERIOUSLY CREEPY.
I BET HE HAD A THING FOR HER!
- THERE ARE SOME MESSED
UP PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD.
WHO WOULD BE INTERESTED IN LUCY?
- I THINK LOKE MIGHT HAVE
A LITTLE CRUSH ON HER.
- NEXT TIME: MY RESOLVE!
- Happy: HER PROSPECTS
AREN'T LOOKIN' GOOD.
THAT MAKES ME WORRY.
- Natsu: AH PLEASE,
SHE'S A LOST CAUSE!
- Happy: YOU'VE GOT A REAL
MEAN STREAK, NATSU!