- Erza: PREVIOUSLY,
ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Happy: BRAIN WENT DOWN,
WHICH MEANS THERE'S ONLY
ONE ORACION SEIS MEMBER LEFT.
- Midnight:
YOU MUST BE DREAMING.
- Happy: A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
ON OUR TEAM FELL INTO A TRAP,
BUT THE BIG BALD GUY
SAVED US!
- YOU ARE DREAMING.
- Erza: I'VE SEEN THE LIGHT
INSIDE YOU
AND IT'S BRIGHTER
THAN EVER BEFORE.
- KEEP ON DREAMING.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WOW, I'M SURPRISED
YOU CAN STAND.
I GET MY REAL FIGHT,
AFTER ALL.  WONDERFUL.
DESTROYING YOU
WILL BE A TREAT.
- I SWEAR ON THIS SACRED BLADE
I WIELD,
I WILL END THIS CHAOS
AND YOUR LIFE TOO.
- NIRVANA WILL NOT BE STOPPED.
OUR TARGET IS GETTING CLOSER--
CAIT SHELTER.
- COME ON, ERZA.
OR SHOULD I CALL YOU TITANIA?
I WANNA SEE YOUR STRENGTH
WITH MY OWN TWO EYES.
BUT I WON'T FEEL IT.
'CAUSE IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN LAND A SINGLE HIT ON ME,
YOU MUST BE DREAMING.
- YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIS REFLECTOR MAGIC.
YOU SAW WHAT IT'S CAPABLE OF.
HE CAN TURN YOUR OWN ATTACK
AGAINST YOU IN AN INSTANT.
- Happy: "ZERO"!
- SHE MOVES SO FAST.
- YOU COULD BE THE FASTEST
PERSON WHO'S EVER LIVED,
BUT YOU'D STILL NEVER
BREAK THROUGH MY REFLECTOR.
IT'S USELESS.
NO!  YOU HIT ME.
- THERE ARE TWO--
TWO CRUCIAL WEAKNESSES
IN YOUR DEFENSE MAGIC.
- THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
HOW DID SHE FIND THEM
IN SUCH A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME?
- ALTHOUGH IT'S TRUE
YOU POSSESS THE POWER
TO BEND WEAPONS
AND EVEN MAGIC ATTACKS,
YOU CANNOT USE THAT ABILITY
TO MANIPULATE THE HUMAN BODY.
IF YOU COULD,
THEN SURELY
YOU WOULD ATTACK MY BODY
RATHER THAN SIMPLY TWISTING
MY ARMOR.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- HA! MAYBE.
BUT WHY WOULD IT MATTER?
I CAN USE ALL
THOSE LOVELY CLOTHES YOU WEAR
TO SQUEEZE YOU
UNTIL YOU POP,
AS FAST OR SLOWLY AS I WANT.
- SO THAT'S ONE WEAKNESS.
ONE MORE.
- ERZA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO MATTER HOW MANY SWORDS
YOU THROW,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO HIT HIM.
- AAH!
- WHILE YOU TWISTED
MY ARMOR EARLIER,
YOU DODGED MY SWORD.
WHY DIDN'T YOU BEND
ITS TRAJECTORY INSTEAD?
IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE ONLY ABLE
TO CONTROL ONE SPACE AT A TIME--
EITHER THE SPACE
SURROUNDING YOUR ENEMY,
OR YOURSELF,
BUT NOT BOTH AT ONCE.
SO WHILE YOUR BENDING SPELL
IS ACTIVE ON ME,
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY
DEFENSELESS,
COMPLETELY UNABLE
TO DEPLOY YOUR REFLECTOR MAGIC
TO REPEL AN ATTACK
THAT'S COMING RIGHT FOR YOU.
- SHE'S FIGURED ALL THAT OUT?
- WHAT'S MORE,
THIS IS MY INFINITY ROBE ARMOR,
BY FAR THE MOST ELASTIC
IN MY COLLECTION,
AND IMMUNE TO YOUR SPELL.
HUH.
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD CONSIDER
THIS ARMOR A THIRD WEAKNESS.
- NO!
IT'S TOO LATE!
- YES,
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
THIS BATTLE HAS REACHED
ITS END.
- ( laughs )
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
TOO LATE FOR YOU.
YOU SHOULD HAVE LET ME
BEAT YOU BEFORE MIDNIGHT,
BEFORE YOU SAW
THE TRUE FACE OF TERROR.
YOU MISSED YOUR ONLY CHANCE
TO REST IN PEACE.
- ( bell tolling )
- WHAT IS THAT?
- SOUNDS LIKE A BELL.
- TOLLING THE MIDNIGHT HOUR.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WHEN THE CLOCK
STRIKES MIDNIGHT,
MY POWERS
REACH THEIR TERRIFYING PEAK!
( laughs )
- WHAT IS HE?
- YOU COULD HAVE PREVENTED
THIS FROM HAPPENING.
- AAH!
( screaming )
- WHAT KIND OF MAGIC IS THIS?
IT'S NOT A TAKEOVER.
IT'S SOMETHING ELSE--
SOMETHING
I'VE NEVER FELT BEFORE.
- JELLAL.
- ( Jellal screaming )
- YOUR REIGN
WAS BASED ON A LIE.
THERE WAS NO FREEDOM
IN THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
EVEN AFTER THE UPRISING,
I WAS STILL TOO AFRAID
TO SLEEP AT NIGHT.
- WHAT?
YOU WERE THERE?!
ALL OF YOU WERE THERE,
IN THE TOWER?
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
WHAT COBRA MEANT.
- DON'T BE SO SMUG, TITANIA!
YOU'RE JUST AS GUILTY
AS HE IS!
WHILE EVERYONE SUFFERED,
YOU TURNED YOUR BACK,
FOR ALL THOSE YEARS.
AND NOW YOU'VE REUNITED
WITH JELLAL,
THE ONE WHO CAUSED
YOUR FRIENDS SO MUCH PAIN.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE HIM.
IN FACT,
YOU'RE EVEN MORE AT FAULT
BECAUSE YOU COULD'VE
STOPPED IT AND YOU DIDN'T.
JUST ASK THEM!
- Erza: GRANDPA ROB.
SIMON!
- ( laughing )
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THINGS
THROUGH THEIR EYES,
WHO IS THE REAL MONSTER HERE?
- SHUT UP!
- OH NO,
YOU'VE DONE IT AGAIN.
YOU'VE KILLED
YOUR DEAREST FRIENDS.
- STOP!
- AAH!
- NO.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
MAKE HIM PAY FOR ALL HE DID.
FINALLY REDEEM YOURSELF.
- OH, I WILL!
( screaming )
- ( all laughing )
- ERZA!
- THIS IS ONLY THE BEGINNING.
THE MIDNIGHT HOUR
IS STILL YOUNG!
- ( bell tolling )
- ( panting )
- HOW?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ONLY A MOMENT AGO,
HE WAS A TOWERING MONSTER.
- MY ILLUSION FAILED ME.
SHE SAW RIGHT THROUGH IT.
- AN ILLUSION?
BUT IT WAS SO REAL,
HORRIFYING.
DID ALL THAT HAPPEN JUST WHILE
THE BELL WAS RINGING?
- ANOTHER WEAKNESS
WOULD BE NOT KNOWING
I'M IMMUNE TO VISUAL MAGIC.
- NO, I'VE LOST.
BUT I'M THE STRONGEST ONE.
I'M THE ULTIMATE MEMBER
OF THE ORACION SEIS,
EVEN STRONGER THAN MY FATHER.
NO ONE CAN TOUCH ME.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
THE GREATEST WIZARD
THAT'S EVER LIVED.
- SOMEONE WHO CAN MOCK THE
SUFFERING OF OTHERS SO CALLOUSLY
HAS A VERY LONG WAY TO GO
TO ACHIEVE GREATNESS.
- ALL I EVER WANTED,
MY PRAYER...
- ( children screaming )
- MY PRAYER WAS TO ONE DAY
FIND A QUIET PLACE
AND FINALLY SLEEP IN PEACE.
- ( gunfire echoing )
- FATHER.
- THIS IS WHO ERZA TRULY IS.
- IF YOU
TRULY DESIRE GREATNESS,
YOU MUST FIRST KNOW
WHAT MAKES YOU WEAK.
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
LIVE WITH AN OPEN HEART.
- ( screaming )
- NATSU!  OKAY.
- HEY, LUCY, DO YOU SEE NATSU
ROLLING ON THE
GROUND OVER THERE?
- ACTUALLY, I'M AFRAID
THAT'S NOT
AN EXTREMELY RARE SIGHT
ON THESE KIND OF MISSIONS.
- I GOT YOU NOW!
- YEAH! NOW THAT WE GOT THIS
CLOWN WHERE WE WANT HIM,
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN--
KEEP THAT THING AWAY FROM ME!
- WELL, GET OUT OF THE WAY,
YOU DUMMY!
- TRY AND HOLD IT STILL,
YA FREAK!
- TRY AND DODGE IT, YA SLOWPOKE!
- WE ALL KNEW THIS WAS COMING.
- AW, I ALWAYS
GET THE CREEPY STARES.
- OH, NO, YOUR EGO IS SHOWING.
- SHUT UP, CAT!
ONCE AGAIN,
MY CUTENESS IS A BURDEN.
OH, POOR ME.
- THE STRESS
IS GETTING TO HER, GUYS!
SHE'S FINALLY
GONE COMPLETELY INSANE!
- AW, I THOUGHT
THERE WAS A REAL WOMAN HERE,
BUT SHE'S JUST A LITTLE GIRL.
- SAY WHAT?!
- LET'S GO!
- OH YEAH!
- A BUNCH OF ANNOYING KIDS.
- GRAY!  NATSU!
- THIS SKULL STICKMAN GUY
ISN'T PLAYIN' AROUND.
- HA!  POOR BABIES.
YOU MAY BE YOUNG,
BUT YOU'VE GOT A LOT TO LEARN
IF YOU WANT TO BEAT ME.
WHO CARES HOW YOUNG YOU ARE?
SO IF YOU WANNA GO
FLAUNTING YOUR TONED,
LIMBER BODIES AROUND LIKE THAT,
FINE. BUT THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMEBODY
HAS SOME SERIOUS
AGE ISSUES AROUND HERE.
- AYE.
- EH?
- NOW WHAT?
- Lucy: THE TRUTH HURTS,
DOESN'T IT?
- Happy:
I DON'T THINK THAT'S IT.
- Klodoa: OH NO.
THIS CANNOT BE.
THEY ALL HAVE FALLEN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THE SIX DEMONS
HAVE BEEN DEFEATED.
THE HORROR!
IT'S IMMINENT.
THE GREAT ONE IS COMING!
- Gray: HUH?
- Natsu: WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
- Lucy: WHO'S COMING?
- I BET WHOEVER
THIS "GREAT ONE" IS,
IT'S NOT GONNA BE
SO GREAT FOR US!
- ( rumbling )
- ( teeth chattering )
- SO WHO ARE YOU
BABBLING ABOUT?
- HE'S GETTING SUPER JUICY.
- THAT'S SWEAT, YA DOPE!
- IT'S BRAIN.
- WHAT?
- THE OLD BALD BRUISER ALREADY
PUT THAT CREEP ON THE GROUND.
- I'M AWARE OF THAT.
BUT WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW
IS THERE'S ANOTHER PERSONALITY
LURKING INSIDE HIM.
YOU'VE SEEN THE OUTER ONE--
"BRAIN," THE NAME FOR THE CALM,
KNOWLEDGE-SEEKING
PERSONA AT THE SURFACE.
BUT THERE IS A HIDDEN FACE
THAT CRAVES ONLY DESTRUCTION.
THEY CALL HIM "ZERO."
- BRAIN WAS BAD ENOUGH
FOR ME.
- ZERO'S WORSE?
- HE POSSESSES INCREDIBLE POWER
PAIRED WITH AN UNQUENCHABLE
THIRST FOR DESTRUCTION.
BUT BRAIN WAS ABLE
TO SEAL HIM AWAY,
USING SIX MAGICAL KEYS.
- Gray: AND THOSE
ARE THE ORACION SEIS?
- CORRECT.
BOUND TOGETHER
USING BODY LINK MAGIC.
AND ONCE
THOSE SIX DEMONS FALL,
ZERO WILL ONCE AGAIN BE FREE
TO ROAM THE LAND,
ANNIHILATING EVERYTHING
WITH THE MISFORTUNE
TO STAND IN HIS PATH.
- OH?
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE A CHALLENGE
TO ME.
- ( moaning )
MASTER ZERO,
I HUMBLY WELCOME YOUR RETURN!
- "MASTER ZERO"?
- THINGS HAVE TAKEN
QUITE AN INTERESTING TURN,
HAVEN'T THEY, KLODOA?
EVEN MIDNIGHT
FELL IN BATTLE.
- PLEASE, SIR, I BEG YOU
TO GRANT ME FORGIVENESS!
- YOU MISUNDERSTAND ME.
I'M NOT DISPLEASED.
ON THE CONTRARY,
IT'S BEEN FAR TOO LONG.
THIS FEELING I HAVE--
THIS FLESH, THIS POWER--
I'VE LONGED FOR IT.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO BEGIN THE TASK
FOR WHICH I WAS SUMMONED.
- YES, SIR!
- YOU SCUM.
YOU'VE DONE AN ADMIRABLE JOB
IN DESTROYING MY GUILD.
BUT AS ITS MASTER,
I AM BOUND BY MY OBLIGATION
TO TAKE MY REVENGE.
- NO WAY.
HE'S THE TRUE LEADER
OF THE ORACION SEIS?
- 'FRAID SO.
- HIS POWER
IS MAKING THE GROUND SHAKE.
- SO ARE YOU FIRED UP
AND READY TO GO, NATSU?
- THE GUY'S GOT SOME CRAZY
MAGICAL POWER GOIN' ON.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO TAKE HIM DOWN.
- HMM. THAT'S IT.
I'LL BEGIN WITH THE BALD ONE
WHO HARMED THIS BODY
WHILE BRAIN
WAS IN CHARGE OF IT.
HIM FIRST!
- YOU'D REALLY ATTACK SOMEBODY
WHO'S NOT EVEN ABLE TO MOVE?
YOU'RE A COWARD.
- NONSENSE.
SPARE ME YOUR FOOLISH IDEALS.
- MY SHIELD--
IT'S NO MATCH FOR HIM.
AAH!
- YOU GUYS!
- OH NO!
- Zero: I TAKE GREAT PLEASURE
IN DESTROYING MANY THINGS
THAT DO NOT MOVE.
WHY SHOULD THAT MAN
BE AN EXCEPTION?
- NOW BURN!
- NOW I'M SCARED.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I'M SO TERRIFIED.
IT'S LIKE I'M STUCK
TO THE GROUND.
THIS IS BAD.
AAH!
- WELL DONE, MASTER ZERO!
VERY WELL DONE.
ONE WAVE OF YOUR HAND
AND THOSE RAPSCALLIONS
WERE SENT SIX FEET UNDER!
- NOT QUITE THE DECISIVE BLOW
THAT WAS NEEDED.
- WHAT?
- THESE VERMIN ARE ALL STILL
CLEARLY BREATHING DOWN THERE,
SO IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
I WON'T BE FINISHED
UNTIL THEY'RE RIPPED TO SHREDS!
- YOU THINK YOU CAN GO ON?
- YES, I CAN MANAGE.
- FORGIVE ME.
IT SEEMS I'VE BEEN BLINDED
BY MY DRIVE TO STOP NIRVANA.
YOU'RE BADLY HURT,
AND ALMOST ALL YOUR MAGIC POWER
HAS BEEN SPENT IN BATTLE.
I NEED TO BE MINDFUL
OF THE STATE YOU'RE IN NOW.
YOU SHOULD REST.
- ERZA, THAT'S KIND,
BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I UNLEASHED NIRVANA
UPON THIS WORLD
AND I MUST DO EVERYTHING
IN MY POWER TO SEND IT BACK.
I HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
- HOW LONG?
I SIMPLY CAN'T HELP
BUT ASK MYSELF.
HOW LONG MUST I CONTINUE
TO FIGHT
THE UNENDING WRONGS
IN THIS WORLD?
- OH, JELLAL.
WHERE COULD HE BE?
I CAN'T FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
- ( both grunt )
- I CAN'T DO THIS MUCH LONGER.
I HAVE TO REST.
- OH, OKAY.
I'M SORRY
FOR PUSHING YOU LIKE THIS.
I KNOW IT MUST BE HARD
TO CARRY ME AROUND.
- DON'T FRET ABOUT IT.
- Wendy: THOSE MOUNTAINS LOOK
PRETTY FAMILIAR, DON'T THEY?
- I'M AFRAID WE'RE GETTING
DANGEROUSLY CLOSE, CHILD.
WHY DOES THIS ANCIENT CITY
HAVE TO BE SO SPRAWLING?
IT'S LIKE LOOKING
FOR A NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
I'M GETTING SCARED.
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN IF WE'RE
NOT ABLE TO FIND HIM IN TIME?
- WE CANNOT ALLOW OURSELVES
TO FIND THAT OUT.
THE STAKES ARE FAR TOO HIGH
TO GIVE UP NOW.
- IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
IT'S THE HARDEST THING EVER,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- YOU MUST START BY FOCUSING
YOUR GOALS, CHILD.
DO YOU WANT
TO CATCH UP WITH JELLAL
OR DO YOU WANT HIM
TO STOP THIS THING?
"CHASE TWO MICE AND YOU'LL
CATCH NEITHER," RIGHT?
- I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WE CAN'T LET NIRVANA
DESTROY OUR GUILD.
- THEN NARROW YOUR FOCUS
ON THAT FOR NOW.
THE REST CAN WAIT.
- YEAH.
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS
IS STOPPING THIS THING
IN ITS TRACKS.
- HA HA! LOOK, MASTER,
THERE IT IS.
OUR NUMBER-ONE TARGET
IS IN SIGHT.
A GIANT SITTING DUCK!
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S IN STORE FOR THEM.  OH!
THOSE DUMMIES IN CAIT SHELTER
ARE IN FOR A BIG SURPRISE.
THEY ARE THE ONES
WHO FIRST DISCOVERED
NIRVANA'S AWESOME POWER
AND THEY JUST SEALED IT
AWAY FROM EVERYONE ELSE.
BUT WE'LL SHOW THEM!
BY WIPING CAIT SHELTER
OFF THE MAP,
WE'LL MAKE SURE THAT NO ONE
MAKES THAT MISTAKE AGAIN.
NIRVANA WILL BE OURS FOREVER.
THIS IS GOING TO BE AMAZING.
- WHAT UTTER NONSENSE.
- WHAT?
- YOU HEARD ME-- NONSENSE.
- AAH!
BUT WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT,
WISE MASTER ZERO?
AAH!
- HA HA HA!
IT'S JUST DESTRUCTION.
THE ONLY THING
I'M AFTER IS DESTRUCTION.
ALL THAT IS STANDING
MUST FALL BY MY HANDS.
I DON'T NEED ANY OTHER REASON.
I YEARN FOR DESTRUCTION.
EVERYTHING IN THIS WORLD
MUST BE DESTROYED!
NOW NIRVANA!  FIRE!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: HEY, NATSU, DO YOU
KNOW WHAT A PEGASUS IS?
- NAH, NOT REALLY, BUT HIBIKI'S
GUILD SEEMS REALLY INTO THEM.
- YEAH, OF COURSE, BECAUSE
IT'S A HORSE WITH WINGS.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE? FIRST
THERE WAS THAT SNAKE WITH WINGS
AND NOW A FLIPPIN' HORSE?
WHY DOES EVERYONE
KEEP COPYING ME?
- I DON'T KNOW. GUESS YOU'RE
KIND OF A TRENDSETTER.
- Both: NEXT TIME--
"FROM PEGASUS TO FAIRIES"!
- Happy: IF EVERYBODY
HAD A WEIRD FLYIN' ANIMAL,
IT'D BE BAD FOR BUSINESS,
YA KNOW?
- Natsu: WAIT A SEC,
WHAT'RE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
WHAT KIND OF BUSINESS
ARE YOU IN?