- HEY, GUYS.
READY FOR SOME
MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- PREVIOUSLY
ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
- Happy: THE PHANTOM LORD
GUILD ATTACKED US.
ERZA USED UP ALL HER
MAGIC ENERGY BLOCKING A BLAST
FROM THEIR CANNON JUPITER
AND NOW SHE'S OUT OF COMMISSION.
SO WE HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO STORM
THEIR GUILD HALL
AND DESTROY THE CANNON
BEFORE IT FIRES AGAIN.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( static charge )
- Happy: HURRY, NATSU!
THE JUPITER CANNON
IS ALMOST READY TO FIRE AGAIN.
- YEAH, I KNOW!
- IT'S TOO LATE.
BLUE FIRE!
- WHOA, THAT WAS
COLD GOING DOWN.
I NEVER TASTED
FIRE LIKE THAT BEFORE.
- SO IT'S YOU,
FAIRY TAIL'S DRAGON SLAYER.
WELL, THIS ISN'T GOING TO
WORK OUT WELL FOR EITHER OF US.
IS IT?
- HUH?
- BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH
IMPERVIOUS TO FIRE ATTACKS.
- I HAVEN'T EVEN HIT YOU YET.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
MY FIRE WON'T HURT YOU?!
- GO AHEAD AND GIVE IT
YOUR BEST SHOT,
BUT YOU WON'T
BE ABLE TO HIT ME.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
FIRE DRAGON...
- I TOLD YOU,
AS THE ELEMENT OF FIRE,
I CAN CONTROL ANY FLAME!
- ...SPIT!
- UGH.
- ( laughs )
I GOT YOU GOOD!
- Happy: TO KEEP FROM
SEEING THOSE TEARS.
- Woman: 15 MINUTES
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- NATSU, YOU GOT TO HURRY.
WE CAN'T LET THE CANNON FIRE.
- THAT WAS A DUMB MOVE.
DO YOU THINK
THIS IS A GAME?
ORANGE FIRE!
- YOU CALL THAT AN ATTACK?
WELL, I CALL IT MY DINNER.
( slurps )
BLEAH! NASTY!
UGH! IT STINKS!
- ( laughs )
IT SMELLS LIKE AN OLD RAG
SOAKED IN SPOILED MILK,
DOESN'T IT?
- THAT'S A DIRTY TRICK.
- AND A FACE
FULL OF SPIT ISN'T?
- Woman: ONE MINUTE
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- COME ON! HURRY UP, NATSU!
- LET GO!
- ( laughs )
NOW YOU WANT TO FIGHT
WITHOUT USING MAGIC.
THAT'S FINE BY ME!
MY KATANA IS AT THE READY.
- ( chuckles )
- YOU THINK YOU'RE SO SMOOTH.
A LITTLE DING LIKE THAT
WON'T DESTROY A GIANT LACRIMA.
- MAYBE NOT, BUT NOW
YOU'RE SWORDLESS,
WHICH MEANS I'VE GOT
THE UPPER HAND.
- GEEZ, HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THAT WON'T WORK.
- ( grunting )
- HOW'D HE DO THAT?
HE EXPANDED THE RANGE
OF HIS FIRE POWER
SO IT WOULD HIT ME.
- Mirajane:
WE ONLY HAVE 30 SECONDS.
- THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
- WHY'S HE TAKING SO LONG?
- OH NO!
WE'RE DEAD MEAT.
- Woman: 20 SECONDS
UNTIL JUPITER FIRES.
- ( growling )
- THINK YOU'RE GONNA
BLAST ME AGAIN?
NOT GONNA HAPPEN!
I'LL KEEP MY DISTANCE
AND CONTROL
YOUR FIRE FROM HERE.
- ( screaming )
- WHAT THE--
I CAN'T GET IT TO MOVE.
IT WON'T EVEN BUDGE.
( strains )
HE'S BLOCKING MY CONTROL.
HOW'D HE FIGURE OUT
HOW TO DO THAT...
IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT?!
- Happy: NATSU!
- THIS IS MY FIRE!
AND I WON'T
LET YOU MESS WITH IT!
- HA! YOUR ATTACK'S NO GOOD
IF YOU CAN'T
HIT YOUR TARGET.
- Woman: THREE, TWO...
ONE...
- OH CRAP.
- WHOEVER SAID
YOU WERE MY TARGET?
- HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
THEY BLEW IT UP.
- YEAH, THEY DID.
THE JUPITER CANNON'S
BEEN DESTROYED JUST IN TIME.
- HE OUTSMARTED ME.
- HEY, BUDDY,
SOMEBODY TAUGHT ME
SOMETHING ABOUT FIRE MAGIC
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
YOU CAN NEVER CONTROL FIRE
IF YOUR HEART ISN'T IN IT.
- Happy: I GET IT.
HE HAD TO TAKE THE TIME
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO OVERCOME TOTOMARU'S
FIRE CONTROL
OR HE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO DESTROY THE CANNON.
NOW I FEEL KIND OF BAD
ABOUT RUSHING HIM LIKE THAT.
- ATTA' BOY, NATSU.  YEAH.
- WATCH OUT.
WE'RE COMING FOR YOU, PHANTOM.
- YEAH, WE GOT THIS.
WIPE OUT THE ENEMY!
- ( cheering )
- DON'T GET COCKY.
YOU HAVEN'T BEATEN ME YET.
AWAKEN THE GIANT!
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU
MESSING WITH MY MAGIC.
PLAY WITH MY FIRE AND
YOU'RE BOUND TO GET BURNED.
YOU GOT ME?!
- ELEMENT CONNECTION SECURED.
- ACTIVATING HORIZONTAL
STABILIZERS.
- ALL WIZARDS IN DANGER ZONE,
EVACUATE!
- THE GIANT AWAKENS!
- HEY, NOW, WHAT
THE HECK'S GOING ON?
- THE WHOLE PLACE IS TILTING.
- HE'S AWAKENING IT RIGHT NOW?
BUT THERE'S NO HORIZONTAL
STABILIZATION IN HERE.
- STABALI-- WHAT?
- ( both grunt )
- OH NO, WHAT'S IT DOING NOW?
- HIP JOINTS STABILIZED.
NOW STANDING.
- YOU FAIRY TAILERS ARE THROUGH.
PHANTOM'S GIANT
WILL SLAUGHTER YOU.
HUH?
- NATSU,
GET UP.
- I CAN'T.
- NO WAY.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
- THE GIANT.
PHANTOM'S MOST
POWERFUL WEAPON.
- Jose: KNEEL BEFORE ME,
YOU DETESTABLE BRATS...
OR YOU FALL VICTIM
TO MY WRATH.
SAVOR YOUR LAST MOMENTS
BECAUSE SOON, I WILL END
YOUR PATHETIC
LITTLE LIVES.
- WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- ( frightened murmurs )
- THEY'RE COMING
TO ATTACK AGAIN.
- GIANTS AND GHOSTS? HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO HANDLE THIS?
- JUST FOCUS ON
THESE THINGS FOR NOW.
WE'LL LET NATSU TAKE CARE
OF THE GIANT FOR US.
- SURE, BUT WHAT ABOUT...
- HIS MOTION SICKNESS?
- ( all groans )
- ( moans )
- COME ON,
YOU GOT TO GET UP.
- WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU GET MOTION SICKNESS?
GUESS YOU CAN'T EAT FIRE
RIGHT NOW, CAN YOU?
WELL THEN, TIME FOR ME
TO FINISH YOU OFF.
- NATSU!
- PREPARE TO DIE,
DRAGON SLAYER!
WAIT.
HEY.  NO!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?!
- YOU'RE NOT A MAN.
YOU'RE A BACKWARDS
SHOOTING SNOWFLAKE!
- Totomaru:
THAT MAKES NO SENSE!
- THANKS, YOU GUYS.
- YOU TWO ARE SO COOL.
YOU SHOWED THAT PHANTOM JERK
WHO'S BOSS.
- WHAT'S YOUR DEAL, NATSU?
THAT WAS JUST SAD.
- IF YOU WERE A REAL MAN,
YOU'D MAKE THE GIANT
MOTION SICK OF YOU.
- SO IS THIS ALL THAT'S LEFT
OF THE JUPITER CANNON?
- AYE.
- THEN YOU DID GOOD.
- HE MUST HAVE STOPPED MOVING
BECAUSE I'M FEELING BETTER NOW.
- I'M GONNA FLY OUTSIDE
AND SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
- ( shouting )
- HEY, LOOK, WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S DRAWING SOMETHING.
- A MAGIC CIRCLE!
- THAT'S THE MAGIC CIRCLE
FOR AN ABYSS BREAK,
ONE OF THE FORBIDDEN SPELLS.
- UH-OH.
- LOOK AT THE SIZE OF IT.
A BLACK WAVE THAT BIG WOULD
WIPE OUT THE ENTIRE CITY.
- WE'RE DOOMED.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
WE GOT TO STOP 'EM.
- I GUESS WE SHOULD SPLIT UP
AND START LOOKING
FOR THIS THING'S
POWER SOURCE, RIGHT?
- MAN, ARE WE EVER GONNA
CATCH A BREAK?
- COME ON,
LET'S DO THIS, GUYS.
- YEAH.
- MIRA, HOW LONG
DO YOU THINK WE HAVE
UNTIL THE GIANT
CASTS THAT SPELL?
- I'D SAY ABOUT TEN MINUTES.
IF ONLY WE COULD FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S POWERING IT.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE THE GUYS INSIDE
ARE LOOKING FOR THE POWER SOURCE
RIGHT NOW.
- SOMEONE'S IN THERE
WITH NATSU?
- YEAH, GRAY AND ELFMAN.
- ELFMAN?! BUT WHY?
- WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
HE WANTED TO GO.
- YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
THAT HE CAN'T FIGHT.
IT'S JUST TOO DANGEROUS.
- HE'LL BE FINE.
HE WAS ONE OF OUR BEST FIGHTERS
IN THE RAID EARLIER.
- FIGHTING GRUNTS IS ONE THING,
BUT IF HE WENT UP AGAINST
ONE OF PHANTOM'S BEST
AS HE IS NOW,
I DON'T KNOW
IF HE COULD HANDLE IT.
- WELL, YEAH,
I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE WORRIED
AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED BACK THEN.
I WOULD BE TOO.
LISTEN, WE ALL
SUFFERED WITH YOU.
BUT I THINK THIS IS HIS WAY
OF TRYING TO LEAVE
THE PAST BEHIND
AND MOVE FORWARD.
LET HIM DO IT.
- Mirajane:
ELFMAN...
FIGHTING TO LEAVE
THE PAST BEHIND.
LISANNA.
I NEED TO START
MOVING FORWARD TOO.
- ( muttering )
- OH NO!
- MIRA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- STOP, DON'T DO IT.
- Man: NO, DON'T!
- Woman: STOP, COME BACK.
- WELL, WELL.
- LEAVE THEM ALONE.
I'M THE ONE THAT YOU'RE AFTER.
I'LL SURRENDER IF YOU SWEAR
TO STOP ATTACKING
OUR GUILD.
- Mirajane:
HOPEFULLY, THIS'LL BUY US
A LITTLE MORE TIME.
- MASTER!
- IS THAT HER?
- ( scoffs )
BE GONE, IMPOSTER.
- Mirajane: HOW'D HE KNOW?
- Jose: ( laughing )
NICE TRANSFORMATION,
BUT YOU CAN'T FOOL ME,
YOUNG LADY.
I KNEW FROM THE START THAT
LUCY HEARTFILIA WASN'T HERE.
- WHAT NOW?
- ( zapping )
- ( yelling )
- I'M USELESS.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING RIGHT.
- Elfman: ( roars )
AS A REAL MAN,
IT'S MY DUTY
TO PROTECT FAIRY TAIL
EVEN IF IT COSTS ME MY LIFE.
- OUI?
SALUT.
- ONE OF THE ELEMENT FOUR.
- Cana: ELFMAN CAN HOLD HIS OWN
AGAINST PHANTOM...
BECAUSE FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS
NEVER GIVE UP WITHOUT A FIGHT.
- ( whimpering )
- ( townspeople shouting )
- ( wizards shouting )
- ELFMAN...
- WHAT THE-- NO!
- ( screams )
( screams )
( grunts )
- Jose: DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOUR LITTLE PARLOR TRICK
WOULD FOOL ME?
AS PUNISHMENT,
I'LL CRUSH YOU TO DEATH
AS YOU WATCH
YOUR FRIENDS PERISH.
- ( murmurs )
- MIRA!
- WE GOT TO GET
HER DOWN SOMEHOW.
- BUT HOW?!
- PLEASE, GUYS.
PLEASE DON'T LET US DOWN.
WE'RE ALL COUNTING ON YOU
TO STOP THAT GIANT.
- ( speaks French )
MY NAME IS SOL,
MONSIEUR SOL.
- LIKE I CARE.
ALL I WANT TO KNOW
IS HOW TO STOP THIS THING.
BEAST ARM!
BLACK BULL!
- WHAT'S THIS? ONLY YOUR
RIGHT ARM CAN TRANSFORM?
IT APPEARS THE RUMORS
FLOATING AROUND
ABOUT YOU ARE TRUE.
- IF YOU DON'T SHUT YOUR TRAP,
I'LL MAKE YOU.
- YOU HAVE A LITTLE SISTER?
( speaks French )
- ( groans )
- NON, NON, NON.
SALUT.
- YOU'RE SERIOUSLY CREEPY.
- NON, NON, NON.
WITH THREE "NON", YOU DON'T
STAND A CHANCE.
- GET OFF ME, MAN-SEWER SOL.
- IT'S "MONSIEUR," IDIOT.
- MAN, HE'S A LOT STRONGER
THAN HE LOOKS.
- MANY YEARS AGO,
YOU ATTEMPTED
A FULL-BODY TAKEOVER
AND FAILED, NO?
YOU WENT BERSERK.
- YOU SHUT UP!
BEAST ARM, IRON BULL!
LISANNA.
- I APOLOGIZE,
BUT I TOOK THE LIBERTY
OF SCANNING YOUR MEMORIES
WHEN YOU SO RUDELY
STEPPED ON ME EARLIER.
( chuckles )
- WHY YOU--
- MY, WHAT AN...
ADORABLE LITTLE
SISTER YOU HAVE.
I GATHERED FROM YOUR MEMORIES
THAT YOU HAVEN'T
SEEN HER IN A WHILE.
OH, PARDONNEZ-MOI.
NOW I SEE THAT SHE WAS BURIED
IN THE COLD, DARK GROUND.
( speaks French )
HOW COULD YOU DO SOMETHING
SO CRUEL TO SOMEONE
WHO LOVED YOU SO MUCH?
- WELL, BIG BROTHER ELF?
- ( strains )
( screams )
I CAN'T LET HIM GET TO ME.
I'VE GOT TO DO THIS.
- NON, NON, NON.
( speaks French )
IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULDN'T ATTEMPT
ANOTHER FULL-BODY TAKEOVER.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TIME YOU TRIED?
YOU LOST CONROL...
- Sol and Lisanna:
BIG BROTHER ELF.
- Lisanna:
IT WAS ALL YOUR FAULT.
HOW COULD YOU FORGET?
I THOUGHT YOU LOVED ME.
PLEASE, DON'T HURT ME.
I ONLY WANT TO HELP YOU.
NO! DON'T DO IT!
( echoes )
- ( speaks French )
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T ATTEMPT
TO DO SOMETHING
YOU KNOW YOU'RE INCAPABLE OF.
ALL YOU'VE DONE IS WASTED
YOUR MAGIC ENERGY.
- YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A COWARD.
A REAL MAN WOULD FIGHT ME
INSTEAD OF
MESSING WITH MY HEAD!
- ARE YOU INSINUATING
I'M NOT A "REAL MAN"?
NON, NON, NON.
HOW DARE YOU
INSULT ME LIKE THAT.
( speaks French )
WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT
TO TELL ME
HOW A "REAL MAN"
SHOULD BEHAVE?
YOU'RE NOT A MAN.
YOU'RE A MONSTER
WHO MURDERED
HIS LITTLE SISTER.
( speaks French )
- ( gasps )
ELFMAN, NO!
ELFMAN!
- BIG SIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW DID THEY
GET AHOLD OF YOU?!
MIRA!
- OH, THAT'S YOUR OLDER SISTER.
MADEMOISELLE MIRAJANE,
ALSO KNOWN AS
"THE SHE DEVIL."
QUITE FEARSOME ONCE,
BUT NOW HOLDS A MERE FRACTION
OF THE POWER SHE ONCE HAD.
( speaks French )
SHE'S BEING PUNISHED FOR
TRYING TO DECEIVE MASTER JOSE.
( speaks French )
...BUT IT WON'T BE LONG
BEFORE SHE'S
CRUSHED TO DEATH.
- RUN! GET OUT OF HERE!
- NO, I CAN'T LEAVE YOU!
- YOU KILLED LISANNA.
AND NOW MIRAJANE WILL DIE
BEFORE YOUR EYES.
IMPOSTER, YOUR MANLY IMAGE
IS JUST A FACADE
HIDING THE WEAK,
POWERLESS WIZARD
YOU REALLY ARE.
A REAL MAN WOULD NEVER LET THAT
HAPPEN TO SUCH FAIR CREATURES.
FOR THAT CRIME, YOU SHALL
RECEIVE ETERNAL TORMENT.
- ( screams )
- SEALING MAGIC:
( speaks French )
YOU WILL BECOME
PART OF THE EARTH
AND RELIVE YOUR PAINFUL MEMORIES
OVER AND OVER AGAIN...
( speaks French )
- NO!
STOP IT!
- ( child crying )
- I KNOW THIS PLACE.
THAT'S ME.
- Lisanna:
BIG BROTHER ELF!
( panting )
- IT'S YOU.  HEY.
LISANNA, I--
- COME ON,
PLEASE TRY TO CHEER UP.
- NO, I CAN'T.
MY PARAKEET'S DEAD AND
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
- IT'S NOT.
YOU HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
EVEN THOUGH
IT MAKES US SAD,
ALL LIVING THINGS
HAVE TO DIE EVENTUALLY.
- REALLY?
EVERYTHING HAS TO DIE?
- IT'S SAD, BUT THAT'S
JUST THE WAY LIFE WORKS.
DON'T WORRY, YOUR FRIEND
WILL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
HE'LL LIVE ON IN YOUR HEART
FOR AS LONG AS YOU
CAN REMEMBER HIM.
- Young and Present Elf:
LIVE ON IN MY HEART?
- SHUT UP!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW I FEEL.
- NO, DON'T GO!
- ( sniffles )
( cries )
- UH, DON'T CRY, LISANNA.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
- ( crying continues )
- GEEZ.
- MIRA.
- DON'T TELL ME YOU TWO
ARE FIGHTING AGAIN?
- OH, HEY, LISANNA.
- NATSU ATE MY WHOLE FISH.
AND HE DIDN'T
EVEN ASK ME FIRST.
- WHENEVER I EAT ANY FISH--
- HOLD ON.
THIS IS THE DAY THAT...
COME ON, LISANNA.
LET'S GO.
WE GOT TO GET TO WORK.
- WHAT? WE JUST FINISHED A JOB.
CAN'T WE TAKE A LITTLE BREAK?
- YEAH, BUT IT'S
AN S-CLASS QUEST.
MIRAJANE WANTS US TO GO ALONG
AND HELP HER OUT WITH IT.
- NO WAY! TOTALLY UNFAIR!
- WHAT KIND OF JOB IS IT?
- AN EMERGENCY REQUEST.
IT JUST CAME IN.
THEY WANT US TO KILL OFF
THIS MONSTER
CALLED THE BEAST.
HEY, YOU WANT TO
COME WITH US, NATSU?
YOU MIGHT LEARN
A THING OR TWO.
- DO WHAT?!
I DON'T WANT HIM TAGGING ALONG.
I'M THE MAN IN THIS FAMILY
AND I CAN PROTECT YOU ON MY OWN!
- OH! WHY YOU GOT TO HOG
ALL THE FUN?!
TAKE ME WITH YOU!
- NO!
YOU CAN'T GO!
YOU'RE NOT READY YET!
AT LEAST TAKE
NATSU WITH YOU!
( gasping )
- ELFMAN, PULL
YOURSELF TOGETHER!
YOU GOT TO
SNAP OUT OF IT!
PLEASE!
ELFMAN!
- ( growling )
- ( gasps )
THAT MONSTER IS ME.
- ( growling )
- Mirajane: ELFMAN,
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER!
- MIRA!
I HAD EVERYONE IN TOWN EVACUATE.
NOW LET ME HELP YOU.
- YOU HAVE TO RUN, LISANNA.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
I WAS GETTING BEAT UP
PRETTY BAD,
SO ELFMAN TRIED TO TAKE OVER
THE BEAST TO PROTECT ME.
- OH MY GOSH, THAT'S HIM?
- IT ALMOST WORKED.
BUT THE BEAST WAS
TOO POWERFUL FOR HIM.
NOW HE'S TOTALLY
LOST CONTROL.
- OH NO.
WHAT DO WE DO?
HOW CAN WE SAVE HIM?
- WE HAVE TO GET HIM
TO COME TO HIS SENSES
BEFORE THE BEAST COMPLETELY
TAKES OVER HIS SOUL.
- ( growls )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
COME BACK HERE!
- BIG BROTHER ELF?
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
IT'S ME, LISANNA,
YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
OUR BIG SISTER MIRA
IS HERE TOO.
WE'RE A FAMILY AND
WHEN TIMES ARE TOUGH,
WE PULL TOGETHER
AND WORK THINGS OUT.
SO WHY DON'T
THE THREE OF US GO HOME
AND TALK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY?
I PROMISE WE'RE
NOT MAD AT YOU.
- IT'S NO USE.
DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME.
JUST RUN!
- COME ON, DON'T BE AFRAID,
BIG BROTHER.
WE STILL LOVE YOU.
- ( silent )
- ( crying )
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT THAT
LISANNA'S DEAD.
- NO, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
REMEMBER WHAT SHE TOLD YOU?
EVEN THOUGH IT MAKES US SAD,
ALL LIVING THINGS
HAVE TO DIE EVENTUALLY.
- YOU WERE THERE THAT DAY?
- LISANNA WILL
CONTINUE TO LIVE ON
INSIDE OUR HEARTS AS LONG
AS WE REMEMBER HER.
- WE WILL.
- FROM NOW ON,
WE'LL LIVE LIFE FOR HER
AND PROMISE
WE WILL NEVER FORGET.
- I'LL NEVER FORGET.
- Mirajane: ELFMAN!
YOU GOT TO SNAP OUT OF IT!
PLEASE, BROTHER,
I CAN'T LOSE YOU TOO!
- NOW IT'S TIME FOR
THE COUP DE GRACE.
- Elfman:
SHE'S CRYING.
- UGH, WHAT NOW?
- I SWORE
I WOULD NEVER LET
ANYONE MAKE YOU CRY AGAIN.
TELL ME!
WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
- THAT LIGHT!
NO, DON'T DO IT, ELFMAN!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
- WHO MADE YOU CRY, MIRA?!
- IMBECILE, YOU'RE NOT
STRONG ENOUGH
TO PERFORM
A FULL-BODY TAKEOVER.
- ( growling )
- MON DIEU!
- ( whimpers )
- ( speaks French )
HE DID IT!
- THE FULL-BODY TAKEOVER!
BEAST SOUL!
- ( growling )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY IS IT JUST ME
OR DOES IT SEEM
LIKE IT'S RAINING INSIDE?
- AYE, IT'S 'CAUSE OUR
GUILD HALL'S FULL OF HOLES
RIGHT NOW THANKS
TO PHANTOM'S ATTACKS.
SO WHEN IT'S A RAINY DAY
LIKE TODAY,
WE END UP WITH A FEW LEAKS.
- IT'S WAY MORE
THAN JUST A FEW LEAKS.
IT'S LIKE FULL-ON RAIN IN HERE.
- KIND OF GIVES THE PLACE
AN ABANDONED-RUINS VIBE, HUH?
- Both: NEXT TIME...
- Natsu: WE'D BETTER START
PATCHING THE ROOF
BEFORE SOMEONE CATCHES A COLD.
- Happy: OH, COME ON,
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
IT'S LIKE A BIG SHOWER.
- MAN, YOU TAKE
POSITIVE THINKING
TO THE EXTREME.