[JUVIA]
Previously, on Fairy Tail.
[GRAY] The battle with
Grimoire Heart continued
on Tenrou Island.
Gramps is still critical,
and the Seven Kin
and their Lost Magic are
wiping the floor with us.
They may have our number
if Bluenote Stinger
decides to join the fight...
Wait a minute... That woman
looks just like my master, Ur!
♪
[JUVIA]
Oh, my beloved Gray...
When we first met you
were my mortal enemy...
But fate had other
plans for us, my love...
We became allies,
and fought side-by-side
in the Tower of Heaven.
After that, I was welcomed
as a new member of
the Fairy Tail guild.
Deep down I've always
known that someday,
I would tie the knot with
my darling ice prince...
but I never imagined
we'd be tied like this.
[HAPPY]
Tears of Love and Vitality!
[MELDY]
With the spell I've cast...
me, you... and your
beloved Gray are all one...
All our senses have merged.
And if one of us were
to die in this battle...
Gray will die as well.
You can't be serious... We all
lose this way... No one lives!
[MELDY] Precisely. That's
how far I'm willing to go.
This is it... Death is
all that's left for us...
Make peace.
[GRAY] What's causing
this horrible pain...?!
I feel like there's
a knife in my gut.
And why do my feet
feel so cold... and wet?!
It must be this thing... Where
the hell did it come from?
Dammit!
If I don't do something quick,
I'm gonna lose her!
[JUVIA] What's this
pressure on my back...?
Is this what my dear
Gray is feeling?
I can sense Gray
Fullbuster's connection...
There's no need
to fight you anymore.
In fact... I'm going
to end this right now!
To do that... I will die!
No, don't!
There is nothing
you can do to stop me!
[JUVIA]
My love... Forgive me!
You hurt yourself... for him?!
You're smart,
I'll give you that...
But causing me
pain won't help...
If you want to stop me,
then you'll have to kill me.
However, doing so will
only aid my vengeance.
Give up... You can't keep
hurting yourself forever...
Eventually your body will fail.
But that doesn't matter
to you, does it...?
You'll fight to
your last breath.
Don't you get it...?! Nothing
you do will change our fate!
All roads converge on death for
us... It's the only option!
No, that's not true... If you
leave Gray alone we'll live!
I used to be a lot like you...
But joining Fairy Tail
has taught me...
even my enemies deserve to live!
Indulgent nonsense! I will
kill Gray Fullbuster...
And put Ultear's heart at ease!
Not if I can help it...
If I have to knock us both out
to stop you, then so be it!
[MELDY]
I have to kill him... For her...
[little girl crying]
[crying]
You don't need to cry anymore.
No one is going to hurt you.
What gives...?
Who's the little brat?
She's a survivor.
Dinner's waiting; just
kill her and be done with it.
I'm going to take her
with us instead.
You gotta be out of
your freakin' mind...!
Master Hades said to find
Zeref's key and then wipe out
everyone in the city;
that means her, too!
She reminds me of myself
when I was a little girl.
I'll take responsibility.
Besides, I have a feeling
she has a great gift
to share with us.
[ZANCROW]
Sure.
[KAIN]
So... dinner?
[MELDY] Ur...? Why do you look
so sad all of the time?
How many times do I have to tell
you not to call me that...?
Ur's my deceased mother...
The name Urtear died with her.
She's dead?
[ULTEAR] I'll tell you
about it... someday.
[MELDY] You are my mother...
Now and forever.
I'm far too young to have such
a mature and talented daughter.
[MELDY]
I have to kill him... For her...
I don't understand...
Why...? Why is she crying?!
You feel love... I can see it!
You love someone... and
they mean the world to you!
[MELDY]
How does she know...?
Did I somehow share my memories
with her through the link?
Please live!
[MELDY]
How is this possible?
Live for her... Please...
Like I live for
the person I love!
You don't have a choice! If you
have love... you have to live!
[MELDY]
Love...
Live... for Ultear...
These feelings...
they're overwhelming.
I can't hold them back.
These tears of love and life
Are unstoppable.
I can't do it...
Please forgive me...
My beloved Gray...
Be safe until I can find you.
[GRAY] That thing on
my wrist disappeared...
And that horrible
pain vanished with it.
Tears?!
Aw, man!
What the hell's goin' on?!
They're gone.
[GRAY]
Stay back!
Were you following me,
little man?
Who are you?
[ULTEAR] Surely you've
noticed the resemblance.
There's a perfectly good reason
that I look so much
like your master, Ur...
I'm her daughter.
[GRAY]
No way... That's impossible...
This is the same woman
who helped Jellal
betray the magic council...
And now she's a member
of Grimoire Heart?
Well, that's news...
So are you here to kill me...?
You must be holdin' a grudge.
No, Gray...
Actually, I've wanted
to meet you for a long time.
Please don't worry...
I'm a friend...
I want to make things right.
Whaddya think?!
[WENDY]
You look cute!
[VIRGO] Clothing from the
Celestial World suits you...
This is our latest
fashion... Like it?
[LUCY]
You bet I do!
[VIRGO] Happy to be of
service... Princess. Your turn.
You didn't have
to do this for me!
Please, think nothing of it...
Now change before
you catch cold.
Okay... Thanks a lot!
Would you like some assistance
getting out of your clothes?
I think I'll be fine...
Thanks for offering.
[LUCY] This rain just
doesn't wanna let up.
It's nice to be dry...
but I feel kinda helpless.
[NATSU] Hey, Carla...!
Did you lose Lily?!
We decided to stop by
base camp on the way here...
Gajeel and Mira are
in pretty bad shape.
So Lily's staying with
them while they recover.
I hope they get better soon.
Me too... but the good news is,
we spotted Grimoire Heart's ship
off the east coast
of the island.
Let's swim over and bust heads.
Hold on, I think we should
go back to base camp first...
If Cana and Gray show up, we
could really use their help.
[WENDY]
She's right...
If it's up for a vote,
then I'm with Lucy,
we should check the camp.
All right... Let's go.
[NATSU]
I'll carry Gramps.
What about me?
Keep the council
from blowin' us up.
Listen we don't want their help;
we can take down Grimoire Heart
and that Zeref creep ourselves!
Tell 'em there's no need
to fire an Etherion blast!
You think they'll listen?
In that case, just try to find
a way to buy us some time.
[NATSU]
We're countin' on you.
Come back...!
You can't beat them!
[DORABOLT] No guild that's
faced Grimoire Heart
has lived to talk about it!
Do you even have a plan?!
Give 'em everything we got.
[NATSU]
That's all!
You're on my side?
[ULTEAR]
That's right.
About, Ur...
I know... You don't
need to say anything.
Her death wasn't your fault...
I don't blame anyone.
[ULTEAR] My mother was simply
protecting her pupils.
I'm very proud of her.
Sure, whatever you say.
This might sound harsh
but I honestly don't care
what you think of me...
And if you're as proud of
her as you say you are...
you've got a funny way
of showin' it!
[ULTEAR]
Are you referring to Zeref?
Damn straight...! If anyone's
responsible for Ur's death,
it's that bastard!
She was killed by Deliora!
A monster that he created!
But instead of getting rid of
him, you're gonna use his power
to kill more people than
any of his creations did!
You have it all wrong, Gray.
[GRAY]
Do I?
Like I said, I'm going
to set it right... Trust me.
This is Ur's will.
Wendy! Can you hear me?!
[AZUMA]
The famous Erza.
Show yourself!
[AZUMA] Finally... I've
found a true warrior...
Titania.
Wendy's gone... I saw to that.
Then you'll die.
To think that even Meldy
would be bested in combat...
I never imagined more than
half of the deadly Seven Kin
would fall to such weak rabble.
I've no choice now.
It would appear
he's already left.
Forgive me, Makarov...
He's the one wizard I hoped
I'd never have to
send into the fray.
The end is near.
Natsu and the others
are headed this way?!
It'll be so good
to see everybody again!
Well... they
should be here soon...
In fact, they're following
Carla to camp as we speak.
[LISANNA]
Oh, thank goodness!
With so many wizards down,
we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
[PANTHERLILY]
We'll be adding one more
to the wounded when
they arrive with Master.
I can't believe those
jerks beat him like that.
I know...
Well they're gonna pay...!
We'll send Grimoire Heart
running for the hills...
If we work together we can
pull it off...! I know it.
[RUSTYROSE] Here's an idea:
why don't you surrender?
Nothing wrong with that,
differences in power abound
in this unbalanced
world of ours.
Feel your drums pound
faster against their cages,
And prepare yourselves...
For oblivion. Because
that's where you're headed.
Oh yeah...? That's what
you think, scoundrel!
I'm worried, Carla...
What if Doranbolt fails?
Just forget about that
creep... We don't need him.
I'm really worried
about Cana, too...
I hope she's made it
back to base camp.
Maybe Erza will be there!
We've got company.
He's strong...
I feel his power!
The rain's pouring down on him
as if there's
a storm cloud over his head!
My "Happy sense"
is startin' to tingle...
Who are you...?!
One of the Kin?
[BLUENOTE] Tell me,
have you learned to fly?
No...? Pity.
Then you'll fall.
I... I can't move!
It's... crushing...
Do you feel that?!
It's overwhelming!
This presence... it's stronger
than the others combined!
It seems an annoyance
has reared its ugly head...
Does he intend to
disturb my glorious feast?
What is that?!
Your death knell...
This war is over.
[AZUMA] Now that Bluenote
has entered the fray...
all life on this island
is as good as gone.
[BLUENOTE]
You know, personally...
Neither the Fairy Tail guild...
nor our plans for Zeref...
mean much of anything to me.
But, there is one thing...
I have been longing
to do on this island.
Where is the grave
of Mavis Vermilion...?
I wish to pay my respects
to Fairy Tail's first master.
[CANA] I've finally found it...!
Mavis' grave!
At last, I'll become
an S-Class wizard...
And then...
I can face my father.
What is this... this light?
It's like fire...
Am I seeing things?!
♪
[HAPPY] Natsu, can I bend
your ear for a second?
[NATSU]
Sure, what's up?
[HAPPY]
I need to 'fess up.
I've been keeping
a really big secret from you.
[NATSU]
'Kay, what is it?
[HAPPY]
You promise you won't get mad?
[NATSU]
Yeah, yeah, I promise.
[HAPPY] Well uh... I, umm...
Are you sure you won't get mad?
[NATSU]
Just spit it out, man!
[HAPPY]
You broke your promise!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next Episode:
The One Thing I Couldn't Say
[NATSU] So, are you
gonna tell me or not?
[HAPPY] No way, Jose!
A secret's not a secret
if you tell
someone else about it.
[NATSU]
Then why'd you even bring it up?