- Narrator: IN A LAND
FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE,
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD
IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST MAGIC IS
MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER INTO
MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS DOT
THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS LEGENDS
HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WILL NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON FAIRY TAIL...
- Mirajane: THE REQUEST BOARD
IS WHERE ALL
THE JOBS ARE POSTED.
PICK ANY ONE YOU WANT.
- Lucy: IT'S THE LITTLE DOGGIE.
- Natsu: OH, MAN, IF WE
DON'T GET BACK TO WORK SOON,
I'M GONNA STARVE.
- HI, I'M LUCY,
A REAL-LIFE WIZARD.
AND THIS BEAUTIFUL CITY
IS MAGNOLIA,
A MAGNIFICENT PLACE FULL OF
MAGIC AND OPPORTUNITIES.
GO RIGHT THROUGH
THE CENTER OF TOWN,
PASS THE LOVELY
KARDIA CATHEDRAL,
AND YOU'LL FIND THE HOME OF
THE CITY'S ONLY MAGICAL GUILD,
FAIRY TAIL.
OH, THIS CUTE LITTLE PLACE
IS MY HOUSE,
A REAL STEAL AT
70,000 JEWEL A MONTH. TRUST ME.
I LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT IT,
FROM THE TUB
TO ALL THE FLOOR SPACE
TO THE AMAZING CLOSETS,
NOT TO MENTION THE ADORABLE
LITTLE RETRO FIREPLACE
AND STOVE.
ISN'T IT JUST DARLING?
BUT WHAT I LOVE MOST
ABOUT IT IS...
MY BEDROOM!
- ( grunts ) - GET THE HECK
OUT OF HERE, YOU JERKS!
- GEEZ, I JUST CAME OVER
TO CHECK OUT YOUR NEW PAD.
- AYE.
- OH YEAH, WELL, WHAT YOU CALL
CHECKING OUT,
I CALL BARGING IN.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE THE POLICE
WOULD CALL IT
"BREAKING AND ENTERING."
- COME ON, WE WERE JUST
TRYING TO BE FRIENDLY.
- THIS IS A SERIOUS
INVASION OF MY PRIVACY.
- NICE PLACE YOU GOT HERE.
- LET'S TRY AND KEEP IT
THAT WAY, ALL RIGHT?!
- HEY, WHAT'S ALL THIS?
- ( gasps )
NOTHING!
- SO YOU JUST KICKED ME
IN THE FACE OVER NOTHING?
- YEAH, MAYBE I WOULD.
NOW WOULD YOU PLEASE
JUST GO HOME?
- OH, BUT YOUR PLACE
IS WAY MORE EXCITING.
- I HATE BOYS.
- Happy: INFILTRATE
THE EVERLUE MANSION.
- LOOK, I JUST MOVED IN
AND I'M NOT READY
FOR GUESTS.
SO HOW ABOUT YOU TWO
JUST DRINK YOUR TEA,
SAY THANKS, AND GET OUT?
YOU GOT THAT?
- TALK ABOUT COLDHEARTED.
- ICE COLD.
- WATCH IT, CAT.
- HEY, I KNOW.
WHY DON'T YOU SHOW
ME AND HAPPY
ALL THOSE WEIRD
LITTLE KEY GUYS
THAT YOU LIKE TO COLLECT.
- FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
THEY'RE CALLED
CELESTIAL SPIRITS.
- HOW MANY OF THESE
CELESTIAL SPIRITS
DO YOU HAVE
CONTRACTS WITH?
- SIX SO FAR.
NOT TO BRAG OR ANYTHING,
BUT I EVEN HAVE A COUPLE
DIFFERENT TYPES OF THEM.
THE SILVER KEYS ARE THE ONES
THAT YOU CAN FIND
IN THE MAGIC SHOPS.
I'VE GOT HOROLOGIUM THE CLOCK,
CRUX THE SOUTHERN CROSS,
AND LYRA THE HARP.
BUT THE GOLD ONES
ARE SUPER RARE.
THERE ARE 12 TOTAL AND THEY
OPEN THE GATES OF THE ZODIAC.
I'VE GOT TAURUS
THE GOLDEN BULL,
AQUARIUS THE WATER BEARER.
THAT LAST ONE IS CANCER
THE GIANT CRAB.
- ( both gasp )
- GIANT CRAB?!
- GIANT CRAB LEGS!
- I'VE NEVER MET ANYONE
AS OBSESSED
WITH FOOD
AS THESE TWO.
THAT REMINDS ME.
I NEED TO MAKE A CONTRACT
WITH THE KEY
I BOUGHT IN HARGEON.
I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU FELLAS
ARE INTERESTED
IN SEEING HOW A CELESTIAL WIZARD
MAKES A CONTRACT WITH
A CELESTIAL SPIRIT.
- I HOPE IT'S NOT SOME
GROTTY BLOOD PACT.
- WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
A PAIN IN THE BUTT TO ME.
- UM, I CAN HEAR YOU,
SO LEAVE MY BUTT OUT OF THIS.
ALL RIGHT, PAY ATTENTION.
I CALL UPON THEE IN THE WORLD
OF THE CELESTIAL SPIRITS.
I BECKON YOU
TO MY SIDE AT ONCE.
PASS THROUGH THE GATE.
- ( circus music plays )
- OPEN,
GATE OF CANIS MINOR.
COME, NICHOLA.
- ( doorbell rings )
- ( gasping )
- NICE TRY.
- SHUT UP!
I MEANT TO DO THAT.
AWW, YOU ARE SUCH
A CUTIE-PATOOTIE.
- YOU THINK SO?
- IT DOESN'T TAKE
MUCH MAGIC POWER
TO GET THESE LITTLE GUYS
THROUGH THE GATE.
SO A LOT OF WIZARDS
ACTUALLY KEEP THEM AS PETS.
- YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE PET THING
DOESN'T SIT WELL WITH ME.
- NOT WITH A WEIRD MASTER
LIKE LOONY HERE.
- MY NAME IS LUCY
AND I CAN STILL HEAR YOU.
WELL, LET'S START WORKING
ON OUR CONTRACT.
- ( warbles )
- ARE YOU FREE MONDAYS?
- MM-MMM.
- TUESDAYS?
- MM-HMM.
- WEDNESDAYS?
- THIS IS BORING.
- MM-HMM.
- GREAT, WELL, THAT
JUST ABOUT DOES IT.
- THAT WAS PRETTY EASY.
- YUP.
- IT MAY SEEM SILLY TO YOU,
BUT IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT.
YOU SEE, A CELESTIAL
WIZARD'S CONTRACT
RELIES ON THE PROMISE
THAT'S MADE
BETWEEN THE WIZARD
AND THE SPIRIT,
WHICH IS WHY
I MAKE IT A POINT
TO ALWAYS KEEP MY PROMISES.
GOT IT?
- OH, YEAH.
- OKAY, NOW, I JUST
NEED TO COME UP WITH A NAME.
- ISN'T IT NICHOLA?
- NO, THAT'S THE SPECIES.
- OH, I KNOW.
COME HERE, PLUE.
- PLUE, HUH?
- I THINK IT'S LIKE
THE CUTEST NAME EVER.
RIGHT, LITTLE PLUE?
- ARE YOU SURE
HE'S COOL WITH THAT?
- WHY WOULDN'T HE BE?
- SO EVEN THOUGH HIS SIGN
IS THE LITTLE DOG,
HE DOESN'T BARK?
THAT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
- WELL, I DON'T HEAR YOU
MEOWING OVER THERE, BUDDY.
WHOA, WHAT'S HE DOING?
- OH, MAN, YOU'RE
RIGHT ABOUT THAT, PLUE.
- YOU CAN UNDERSTAND HIM?
WHAT IS YOUR DEAL?
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN IT'S SETTLED.
YOU'RE BOTH GONNA BE
A PART OF OUR TEAM.
- GO TEAM!
- YOUR TEAM?
- AYE, EVEN THOUGH
EVERYBODY IN THE GUILD
IS ALLIED TO ONE ANOTHER,
SOME MEMBERS THAT
GET ALONG REALLY WELL
GET TOGETHER AND FORM TEAMS
WITHIN THE GUILD.
THAT WAY, JOBS THAT MAY BE
TOO HARD FOR ONE PERSON TO TAKE
CAN GET DONE BY A TEAM.
- AWESOME, LET'S DO IT.
- COOL, SO YOU'RE GONNA
WORK WITH US?
- YEP, YOU HAVE MY WORD.
- RIGHT ON.
- OKAY, TEAM, THEN
LET'S GET TO WORK.
I'VE GOT OUR FIRST JOB
RIGHT HERE.
- IT'S ALL HAPPENING SO FAST.
LET ME SEE WHAT YOU GOT THERE.
SO IT'S IN SHIROTSUME, HUH?
NO WAY!  200,000 JEWEL
JUST FOR TAKING A BOOK
FROM SOME RICH GUY
NAMED DUKE EVERLUE.
- SHOULD BE A PIECE OF CAKE,
RIGHT?
- "PLEASE NOTE:
EVERLUE'S A DIRTY OLD MAN
WHO'S CURRENTLY LOOKING
FOR MAIDS WITH BLOND HAIR."
- WE KNOW A BLOND-HAIRED GIRL,
DON'T WE?
- YUP, AND I BET WE CAN
FIND HER A MAID'S UNIFORM.
- WHY YOU SNEAKY LITTLE--
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
- IT'S A GOOD THING
THAT CELESTIAL WIZARDS
NEVER GO BACK ON THEIR WORD
'CAUSE NOW YOU'RE STUCK WITH US.
- Lucy: BUT YOU TRICKED ME!
- Natsu: OH, LIGHTEN UP,
WOULD YOU?
NOW TRY GETTING INTO CHARACTER
AND ADDRESS HAPPY HERE
AS YOUR MASTER.
- NO WAY!
- UGH! DARN.
DID SOMEBODY ALREADY TAKE
THAT BOOK-STEALING GIG?
THAT ONE PAID 200,000.
- SORRY, I GUESS NATSU
AND LUCY GOT TO IT FIRST.
- ( sighs ) I REALLY
COULD HAVE USED THAT MONEY.
- DON'T DESPAIR.  IT'S PROBABLY
FOR THE BEST, LEVY.
IT'S CHANGED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I WAS JUST CONTACTED
BY THE CLIENT
CONCERNING THAT JOB.
- OH, DID THEY CANCEL IT?
- NO.
QUITE THE OPPOSITE.
IN FACT, THE REWARD
HAS BEEN INCREASED.
IT'S NOW...
- 2 MILLION JEWEL?!
- THEY PAID THAT MUCH
FOR SOME STUPID BOOK?
- THAT'S ALMOST LIKE
FIGHTING MONSTERS KIND OF PAY.
- DID THEY GIVE
ANY REASON WHY?
Droy: MAYBE WE'RE
LUCKY WE MISSED IT.
Jet: LET'S FIND
SOMETHING EASIER.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE THIS JOB
JUST GOT INTERESTING.
- OH, GRAY, NICE SKIVVIES.
- HMM?
( screams )
- ( snorts )
- ARE YOU ENJOYING
YOUR CARRIAGE RIDE
TODAY, MASTER?
ANYTHING I CAN GET FOR YOU?
- I COULD REALLY USE
A BARF BAG RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- I'M PLAYING
THE PART OF THE MASTER
SO I SHOULD BE
GIVING THE ORDERS.
- SHUT UP, YOU STUPID FELINE!
OH, HEY, NATSU?
- WHAT'S UP?
- I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHY YOU PICKED ME
TO JOIN YOUR TEAM. - 'CAUSE YOU
SEEM LIKE A NICE PERSON.
- WHOA, DID I ACTUALLY JUST GET
A COMPLIMENT FROM THIS GUY?
- BUT YOU'RE JUST SO WEIRD.
- THE FIRE-EATER WITH
THE TALKING CAT
THINKS I'M WEIRD?
ANYWAY, I'M TOTALLY STOKED
ABOUT MY FIRST REAL JOB.
I KNOW I'M GONNA ROCK IT.
- REALLY?  I THOUGHT
YOU WERE UPSET ABOUT IT.
- YEAH, I WAS MAD AT FIRST,
BUT IF THIS PERV
LIKES PRETTY GIRLS,
I'M PERFECT FOR THE JOB, RIGHT?
( giggling )
- ALL YOU HUMANS
KIND OF LOOK ALIKE TO ME.
- Lucy: I THINK IT'S TIME
WE WORKED OUT OUR PAY SCALE.
SINCE I'M DOING ALL THE WORK,
I THINK WE SHOULD
SPLIT THE REWARD
80, 10, AND 10.
- Happy: YOU ONLY WANT 10%?
- I'M THE 80!
- THEN...
- Narrator:
THE TOWN OF SHIROTSUME.
- THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I'M RIDING IN ONE OF THOSE.
- YOU SAY THAT EVERY TIME.
- MAN, I'M STARVING.
- CAN'T YOU JUST
EAT YOUR OWN FIRE?
- OH, YEAH,
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
EAT PLUE OR YOUR COW
WHILE WE'RE AT IT? - WHY WOULD
I DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- IT'S KIND OF THE SAME THING.
- SO LET ME
GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU CAN EAT FIRE,
BUT JUST NOT YOUR OWN?
THAT'S KIND OF LAME.
- WHOA, LET'S STOP
AND GET A BITE.
- NAH, I'M ALL RIGHT,
BUT YOU TWO ENJOY.
- WHAT IS IT WITH HER?
WE SHOULD BE EATING
TOGETHER AS A TEAM.
- OH WELL.
- ( both chewing )
- BE SURE THAT YOU SAVE
ALL THE FAT STUFF FOR LUCY.
- YEAH, FROM
THE LOOKS OF HER,
THAT'S WHAT SHE LIKES THE MOST.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, CAT.
WHAT THE HECK
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- HEY.  LUCY?
- COME ON.
DON'T BE SHY, BOYS.
I KNOW I LOOK SUPER CUTE
IN THIS UNIFORM.
- ( gasps )
- HAVE YOU HAD
ENOUGH FOOD, MASTER?
OR SHALL I
BRING YOU SOME MORE?
YOUR WISH IS MY COMMAND.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
WE WERE JOKING
ABOUT THE COSTUME,
BUT SHE TOOK IT SERIOUSLY.
- I GUESS WE'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO GO ALONG WITH IT.
DON'T SAY ANYTHING, OKAY?
- I CAN HEAR YOU!
- MY NAME'S KABY MELON.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
- HE SAID MELON. - OH, MAN,
YOU HAVE A TASTY NAME.
- QUIT BEING RUDE, GUYS.
- ( laughs ) DON'T WORRY.
I GET THAT A LOT.
- WHY DOES HIS NAME
SOUND FAMILIAR?
- WELL, FIRST THINGS FIRST.
ALLOW ME TO TELL
YOU ABOUT THE JOB.
- GO ON.
- YEAH.
- IT'S PRETTY
STRAIGHT FORWARD, REALLY.
DUKE EVERLUE HAS A BOOK
CALLED "DAYBREAK"
IN HIS POSSESSION.
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO BURN IT
FOR ME. - NO PROB.
I'LL BURN THE WHOLE PLACE
DOWN IF YOU WANT.
- HE LIKES FIRE. - I'M NOT
GOING TO JAIL FOR ARSON
BECAUSE OF THE TWO OF YOU.
MAY I ASK WHY, SIR?
- FOR 200,000 JEWEL,
WHO THE HECK CARES?
- THE REWARD HAS BEEN
RAISED TO 2 MILLION.
- ( all gasp )
2 MILLION?!
- I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE AWARE
THE AMOUNT HAD CHANGED.
- 2 MILLION SPLIT THREE WAYS?
WOW! I STINK AT MATH,
BUT THAT'S A LOT!
- WAIT, I GOT IT.
I GET 1 MILLION.
YOU GET 1 MILLION.
AND LUCY GETS ALL THE REST.
- THAT SURE SOUNDS
FAIR TO ME.
- AYE. - BUT THAT
LEAVES ME WITH NOTHING.
WHY'D YOU RAISE THE REWARD?
- WELL, BECAUSE IT MEANS
THAT MUCH TO ME.
THAT BOOK MUST BE DESTROYED,
NO MATTER THE COST.
- AH!
- OH YEAH!
I AM FIRED UP NOW.
LET'S DO THIS, LUCY.
- HEY, WAIT A SEC.
- "DAYBREAK..."
IT MUST BE BURNED.
IT CANNOT BE ALLOWED
TO EXIST ANY LONGER.
- Narrator: WELCOME
TO DUKE EVERLUE'S MANSION.
- EXCUSE ME, I HEARD
YOU HAD AN OPENING
FOR A MAID POSITION.
HELLO?
WOW THIS GEEZER
WITH MY LOOKS,
BURN SOME STUPID BOOK,
AND COLLECT 2 MILLION JEWEL.
THIS'LL BE SWEET.
- DON'T SCREW UP, OKAY?
- BREAK A LEG.
- ( screams )
- SO YOU'RE A MAID?
- YEAH.
- I ASSUME YOU'RE HERE
'CAUSE YOU SAW THE AD
THAT THE MASTER
PLACED IN THE PAPER.
- BOYOYOYO.
DID I HEAR SOMEONE SAY "MASTER"?
- MORE LIKE MONSTER.
- LET'S SEE HERE.
- WELL, I SURE HOPE
YOU LIKE WHAT YOU SEE.
- ( grunts ) - OH, MAN,
HE IS CREEPING ME OUT.
STAY STRONG, LUCY.
- I'LL PASS.
NOW SCRAM, UGLY.
- YOU HEARD THE MAN.
GET GOING, UGLY.
- SORRY.
BUT A MAN OF MY STANDING
HAS CERTAIN STANDARDS
TO UPHOLD.
THAT'S WHY I ONLY HIRE
THE FAIREST OF THE FAIR.
- HUH?
- OH, YOU'RE THE BEST, MASTER.
- I'VE NEVER MET SUCH
A KIND-HEARTED MAN.
- I THINK YOU'RE
THE SWEETEST GUY ALIVE.
- WHY DON'T YOU
RUN ALONG HOME, UGLY?
- ( cries )
- JUST COULDN'T DO IT, HUH?
- I TRIED!
BUT THAT IDIOT
WOULDN'T KNOW BEAUTY
IF IT BIT HIM
IN THE BEHIND.
- UH-HUH.
- ( cries )
THIS STINKS.
- OKAY, I GUESS
WE'LL HAVE TO RESORT
TO OLD PLAN T.
- YEAH, THAT BIG FAT JERK'S
GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
WAIT A SEC,
WHAT'S PLAN T?
- Happy: TAKE 'EM BY STORM.
- THAT'S NOT A PLAN.
- ( Everlue chuckles )
SO IT SEEMS WE HAVE
ANOTHER GROUP OF WIZARDS
AT OUR DOOR.
AND THESE
ARE FROM FAIRY TAIL.
- WHOOPSIE DAISY.
- THANKS A LOT, HAPPY.
- AYE.
- GEEZ.
THIS ISN'T REALLY TAKING
'EM BY STORM, YOU KNOW.
I THINK WE SHOULD
HAVE JUST
BUSTED RIGHT IN THROUGH
THE FRONT DOOR.
- WHAT DID I TELL YOU BEFORE?
I'M NOT GOING TO JAIL
'CAUSE OF YOU.
- YEAH, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU WERE OUT
TO GET REVENGE ON THIS GUY.
- OH, I'LL GET MY REVENGE.
- NOT ONLY AM I
GONNA BURN HIS BOOK,
BUT I'M GONNA USE HIS TOOTHBRUSH
TO CLEAN THE TOILET.
- THAT IS TOTALLY GROSS.
- TOTALLY.
- WHOA, IS THIS SOME KIND
OF WEIRD STOREROOM?
- RAAWR!
CHECK ME OUT!
- YEAH.
YOU'RE LOOKING FIERCE, HAPPY.
- ( doorbells ring )
- ( toilet flushes )
- ARE WE GONNA HAVE TO SEARCH
EVERY ROOM IN THIS WHOLE
STINKING PLACE? - WELL, YEAH.
- I THINK WE SHOULD
TAKE A HOSTAGE
AND FORCE THEM TO TELL US
WHERE THE BOOK IS.
- AYE.
- KIND OF THE WHOLE IDEA HERE
IS NOT TO BE SEEN,
YOU DUMMY.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE STEALTHY,
LIKE A NINJA.
- LIKE A REAL NINJA.
- WHAT'S GOING ON INSIDE
THAT HEAD OF YOURS?
- INTRUDER ALERT, VIRGO!
- LET'S CRUSH 'EM, GIRLS.
- Lucy: WE'RE TOAST.
- AAH!
- IT'S A MONSTER!
- ( whimpers )
- NINJA POWER!
- FLYING VIRGO ATTACK.
- WHOA!
- OH NO!
HEY, YOU COULD TAKE OFF
THAT MASK NOW.
- ( straining )
- ( grunts )
- WE MUSTN'T LET OURSELVES
BE DISCOVERED.
WE ARE NINJA.
- NINJA.
- NINJAS ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE QUIET, GUYS.
- WHOA, THERE ARE MANY BOOKS
IN THIS LIBRARY.
- AYE, THERE ARE, INDEED.
- WOW, WHO WOULD
HAVE THOUGHT
THAT EVERLUE'S
A MAJOR BOOKWORM?
- LET'S START LOOKING.
- AYE, SIR.
- ( sighs )
HOW ARE WE EVER GONNA FIND
ONE STUPID BOOK
IN THIS PLACE? - OOH, THIS ONE
HAS LOTS OF PICTURES.
- LOOK, IT'S A BOOK ON FISH.
- CHECK OUT THIS ONE.
IT'S SPARKLY.
- ( laughs )
- HEY, WOULD YOU GET SERIOUS
AND START LOOKING
FOR THE BOOK WE NEED?
( gasps )
IT'S "DAYBREAK."
- Happy: HAVE WE BEEN HERE
THAT LONG?
- YOU FOUND IT.
- NATSU FOUND IT.
- I DID? - 2 MILLION JEWEL,
HERE WE COME.
- LET'S SPARK IT UP.
- THAT WAS SO EASY.
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
THIS WAS WRITTEN
BY KEMU ZALEON.
- ZALE-WHAT?
- ZALEON WAS A GREAT WIZARD
AND AN AMAZING NOVELIST.
I'M SUCH A BIG FAN.
I WAS TOTALLY POSITIVE
THAT I'D READ
EVERY SINGLE SENTENCE
HE'D EVER WRITTEN,
BUT THIS MUST BE
AN UNPUBLISHED NOVEL.
- OH, YEAH, WHO CARES?
IT ALL BURNS THE SAME TO ME.
- DON'T YOU DARE TOUCH IT.
THIS IS A GREAT
WORK OF LITERATURE.
YOU BETTER STAY
AWAY FROM IT, PYRO.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT OUR MISSION?
- JUST FORGET ABOUT
THE STUPID MISSION.
- FAILURE IS NOT AN OPTION.
- COME ON YOU GUYS,
LET'S JUST SAY WE BURNED IT.
I'LL KEEP IT A SECRET,
I SWEAR.
- I'M NOT A LIAR.
- AYE.
- Everlue: WELL, WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
SO YOU THIEVES ARE LOOKING
TO PILFER "DAYBREAK" FROM ME,
ARE YOU?
BOYOYO.
- SEE, SLOWPOKE,
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
- UM, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- DON'T YOU THINK
IT'D BEEN WAY EASIER
JUST TO COME IN
THROUGH THE DOOR?
- I KNEW ALL YOU LOWLIFE
WIZARD TYPES
WERE COMING AROUND HERE
TO TAKE SOMETHING OF MINE.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE GUESSED
IT WAS THAT STUPID BOOK.
- STUPID? - THIS BOOK
MUST BE IMPORTANT
IF THE CLIENT IS WILLING
TO PAY SO MUCH TO DESTROY IT.
SO I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY WOULD EVERLUE
SAY THAT ABOUT IT?
THIS WORKS OUT GREAT.
IF IT'S SO STUPID,
I GUESS IT'S FINE
IF I KEEP IT.
- IT'S MINE!
YOU CAN'T HAVE IT.
SO GET YOUR GRUBBY HANDS OFF.
- GREEDY GUT.
- SHUT YOUR TRAP, UGLY.
- WOULD YOU HAND OVER THAT BOOK
AND LET ME GET THIS OVER WITH?
- NO WAY, I'M NOT
GIVING IT TO YOU.
- LUCY, THIS IS OUR JOB!
- WELL, AT LEAST
LET ME READ IT FIRST.
- All: READ IT NOW?!
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
HOW DARE YOU
PUT YOUR FILTHY HANDS
ON MY POSSESSIONS.
NOW, COME FORTH,
VANISH BROTHERS.
- YOU CALLED UPON US, SIR?
- CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT
THESE LITTLE PUNKS
ARE FROM THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD?
TALK ABOUT A BUNCH OF RUNTS.
- THAT SIGN MEANS THEY'RE FROM
THE SOUTHERN WOLVES.
IT'S A MERCENARY GUILD.
- SO YOU GOT BODYGUARDS,
DO YOU?
- OH WOW.
- BOYOYOYO, THE SOUTHERN WOLVES
ARE ALWAYS HUNGRY
FOR FRESH GAME.
SAY YOUR PRAYERS, THIEVES.
- HEY, TRY AND HOLD
THEM OFF FOR A WHILE.
I'M NOT SURE, BUT
I THINK THIS BOOK
HOLDS SOME KIND OF SECRET.
- RIGHT.
- A SECRET?
IT MUST HAVE SLIPPED BY ME
SOMEHOW.
IT COULD BE A TREASURE MAP
OR SOMETHING.
I'M GOING AFTER THE GIRL.
MAKE SURE PINK HAIR DOESN'T
LEAVE HERE IN ONE PIECE.
- Both: YES, SIR.
- HAPPY, GO ON AND HELP LUCY.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU
DON'T NEED ME HERE?
- NO, THANKS,
BUT I'LL BE JUST FINE.
- WHOA, YOU SURE TALK BIG
FOR SUCH A LITTLE GUY.
- PERHAPS WE SHOULD
PUT HIM IN HIS PLACE.
SO YOU'RE A FIRE WIZARD.
- YEAH, BUT HOW'D
YOU KNOW THAT?
- WE SAW THE FIRE
AROUND YOUR LEGS
WHEN YOU WERE
FIGHTING VIRGO.
- SO IT'S OBVIOUS THAT YOU'RE
AN ABILITY-TYPE FIRE WIZARD.
- Narrator:
AN ABILITY-TYPE WIZARD
USES MAGIC THAT FLOWS
THROUGH THEIR BODY.
A WIZARD LIKE LUCY,
WHO USES ITEMS
THEY'VE COLLECTED,
IS CALLED
A HOLDER-TYPE WIZARD.
- SO I GUESS YOU KNOW WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN YOU PLAY WITH FIRE.
YOU GET BURNED!
- I'M SORRY TO
BREAK IT TO YOU, KID,
BUT FIGHTING FIRE WIZARDS
IS SOMETHING WE DO WELL,
VERY WELL.
- FAIRY TAIL MAY BE
A BIG-TIME GUILD AND ALL,
BUT YOU PATHETIC WIZARDS
ARE NO MATCH
FOR TRAINED
MERCENARIES LIKE US.
- HA, IF THAT'S YOUR BEST,
THEN YOU'RE DEAD WRONG.
- WHOA, THIS KID REALLY
THINKS HE CAN BEAT US.
- DO YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW WHAT
A WIZARD'S GREATEST WEAKNESS IS?
- ( gasps ) YOU TALKING ABOUT
MOTION SICKNESS?!
- UM, I THINK THAT MIGHT BE
MORE OF A PERSONAL PROBLEM.
- IS HE MAKING FUN OF US?
- THEIR WEAKNESS
IS THEIR BODIES.
SINCE WIZARDS HAVE
TO FOCUS SO INTENSELY
ON HONING THEIR
MENTAL ABILITIES...
- THEY NEGLECT TO
TRAIN THEIR BODIES,
WHICH LEAVES THEM
PHYSICALLY WEAK.
- ON THE OTHER HAND,
WE FOCUS ON OUR
PHYSICAL ABILITIES.
- SO WE HAVE MORE POWER
AND SPEED THAN YOU.
- OH, I AM SO SCARED.
NOW STOP YOUR BLABBING
AND LET'S DANCE.
- HEY, BRO', COMBO ATTACK?
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- Both: HEAVEN AND EARTH
ANNIHILATION !
- BRING IT ON!
- Narrator: LUCY IS USING
HER WIND-READER GLASSES.
THEY ALLOW THE USER TO READ
AT MIND-BOGGLING SPEEDS.
- THAT'S AMAZING.
I KNEW THIS BOOK HELD
SOME SORT OF SECRET.
( gasps )
- WELL, THEN, PLEASE SHARE.
SECRETS DON'T MAKE FRIENDS,
YOU KNOW.
- NO WAY.
A MAN LIKE YOU
DOESN'T DESERVE
TO KNOW WHAT IT IS.
YOU'RE AN ENEMY OF LITERATURE.
- ( both screaming )
- LOOK TOWARDS HEAVEN
AND I STRIKE FROM THE EARTH.
- LOOK TOWARDS EARTH AND WE
STRIKE DOWN FROM HEAVEN.
- YOU HAVE WITNESSED
THE TRUE POWER
OF THE VANISH BROTHERS,
THE HEAVEN AND EARTH
ANNIHILATION TECHNIQUE.
- IT'S A FORCE THAT VERY FEW
ARE ABLE TO SURVIVE.
( gasps )
- GUESS I'M ONE OF THE FEW.
SORRY, GUYS.
- NO WAY.
- I'M GONNA BLOW YOU AWAY!
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- HA, FIRE MAGIC?
- WE'VE GOT HIM.
FLAME COOKING!
YOU SEE, MY FRYING PAN
ABSORBS YOUR FLAMES
AND DOUBLES THEIR STRENGTH...
RIGHT BACK AT YOU.
AH!
- NOW HE'S
A FLAME-COOKED FAIRY.
- GOOD-BYE, KID.
- ( screaming )
NO!
- OH, YEAH.
NOW I'VE GOT SOME
FIRE IN MY BELLY.
LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
- ( gasping )
- UH-OH.
DID I OVERDO IT AGAIN?
- ( singing in Japanese )
Mirajane: BOYOYOYO,
MIRAJANE IS AT YOUR SERVICE.
Lucy: WHAT THE HECK
DID YOU JUST SAY?
- I'M JUST HOPING THAT
EXPRESSION
WILL CATCH ON
IN FAIRY TAIL.
- WELL, I REALLY HOPE
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN.
- OH, COME ON.
DON'T BE A DOWNER, LUCY.
IT'S SO CUTE AND
SO MUCH FUN TO SAY.
BOYOYOYOYO!
- STOP IT, MIRA,
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT!
Both: NEXT TIME...
Mirajane:
I BET WE'RE GONNA HEAR MORE
BOYOYOYOYO'S ON
THE NEXT EPISODE.
- Lucy: I DON'T KNOW IF
I CAN HANDLE MUCH MORE.