- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Happy: THE S-CLASS WIZARD
PROMOTION TRIAL FINALLY BEGUN.
IN THE FIRST ROUND, EACH TEAM
HAD TO CHOOSE A ROUTE
WHERE THEY'D HAVE TO FIGHT
ANOTHER COMPETING TEAM
OR AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
UNFORTUNATELY,
NATSU ENDED UP WITH GILDARTS.
- YEAH, HE'S JUST LUCKY I WENT
EASY ON HIM, YOU KNOW? (laughs)
- THAT WAS CONVINCING.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- TENROU ISLAND
IS JUST UP AHEAD.
- DO YOU THINK MASTER MAKAROV
WILL BE ANGRY WITH US
FOR FOLLOWING THEM HERE?
- I DOUBT THAT HE'LL BE ANGRY.
WE'RE JUST TAKING A LOOK AROUND.
- I ASSUME WE'RE HERE BECAUSE
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT WENDY.
- SHE KNEW I WAS FIRMLY
AGAINST THE IDEA,
BUT SHE WENT
AND DID IT ANYWAY.
- Lucy: MEST!
- A WEEK'S PASSED BUT I REMEMBER
IT LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
- SKY MAIDEN.
- AND YOU ARE?
MY NAME'S MEST GRYDER,
AND I WAS ONCE MYSTOGAN'S PUPIL.
- SERIOUSLY?
I HAD NO IDEA.
I'M SURPRISED MYSTOGAN NEVER
MENTIONED ME
'CAUSE HE TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU.
- EXCUSE ME, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHAT FRESH SNOW TASTES LIKE
DON'T MIND ME, WENDY.
- OKAY.
- HE'S SO ODD.
- I KNOW WE JUST MET,
BUT I NEED YOUR HELP.
- IF YOU'RE GOING TO
ASK HER FOR HELP,
YOU COULD AT LEAST
LOOK HER IN THE EYES.
- SORRY.  I TEND TO GET
DISTRACTED WHENEVER I WANT
TO KNOW ABOUT SOMETHING.
IT'S A REALLY BAD HABIT,
BUT I CAN'T SEEM TO BREAK IT.
PLEASE, WENDY.
PLEASE SAY YOU'LL HELP ME.
WITH YOU BY MY SIDE, I KNOW
I'LL BECOME AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
SO WILL YOU DO IT?
WILL YOU HELP ME?
- ME?  BUT, MEST,
I'M NOT THAT STRONG.
- THE ANSWER IS OBVIOUSLY NO.
- HMM.
I HAD TO DO IT.
I HAD TO KNOW WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO FLOAT IN A RIVER
IN THE MIDDLE OF WINTER.
- I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU TO
PARTNER WITH THIS CRETIN, WENDY.
- HE'S WEIRD, BUT HE DOESN'T
SEEM LIKE HE'S A BAD PERSON.
- HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I JUST SHOULD
HELP HIM FOR MYSTOGAN'S SAKE.
HE DID SO MUCH FOR ME
AND I NEVER GOT TO REPAY HIM.
- BUT YOU'VE DONE MORE
THAN ENOUGH, CHILD.
YOU HELPED SAVE EDOLAS.
- ONLY BECAUSE THE OTHERS
WERE THERE WITH ME
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
ON MY OWN.
I FEEL LIKE I OWE HIM
SO MUCH MORE.
- NO, DON'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT IT.
SO IN THE END,
SHE IGNORED ME.
CLAIMING SHE NEEDED
TO HELP MEST IN ORDER
TO REPAY HER DEBT
TO MYSTOGAN.
- AND THAT'S THE REASON
THE TWO OF YOU DIDN'T SPEAK
TO EACH OTHER
FOR AN ENTIRE WEEK?
- SHE'S MORE STUBBORN
THAN SHE LOOKS, LILY.
- SAME GOES FOR YOU.
- IN ALL HONESTY,
I COULDN'T CARE LESS ABOUT HER
TEAMING UP WITH THAT CREEP MEST.
IT'S THE TRIAL ITSELF
THAT HAS ME ON EDGE.
I'VE GOT A REALLY
BAD FEELING ABOUT IT.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S
YOUR CLAIRVOYANCE?
- I'M NOT SURE. IT'S
ALL SO DISJOINTED
THAT IT'S HARD FOR ME TO SAY.
- PERSONALLY, I THINK WE NEED TO
KEEP AN EYE ON THIS MEST FELLOW.
HE SAID HE WAS
MYSTOGAN'S PUPIL,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
SIT WELL WITH ME.
- YOU TWO. I WANT TO KNOW,
DO YOUR SKILLS WARRANT
SUCH COCKINESS?
- BE CAREFUL.
HERE THEY COME.
- I DON'T GIVE
A CRAP ABOUT MEST,
BUT I FEEL BAD ABOUT
KICKING YOUR BUTT, WENDY.
- I AIN'T GOING EASY
ON YOU, KID.  ICE MAKE HAMMER.
SNEAK ATTACK, HUH?
- GRANT ME THE POWER
OF THE HEAVENS.
SKY DRAGON ROAR.
- O, REGULUS.
LEND ME YOUR STRENGTH.
I HAD NO CLUE
YOU WERE THIS POWERFUL.
- I GOT YOUR BACK.
ICE MAKE FLOOR.
THAT JUST LEAVES YOU, WENDY.
TOLD YOU I AIN'T
GOING EASY ON YOU.
ULTIMATE SECRET ART.
EAT A BUNCH OF PICKLED PLUMS.
( groaning )
- ( shouts )
THEY'RE SO SOUR THAT JUST
THE SIGHT OF THEM
MAKES MY LIPS START TO PUCKER.
THIS MUST BE SOME SORT
OF TELEPATHY MAGIC.
I'D BETTER RUN.
- THE ZENITH OF REGULUS.
- ( screaming )
- ( groaning )
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
ELFMAN AND EVERGREEN
ARE FORCED TO FACE OFF
AGAINST HIS SISTER,
THE S-CLASS WIZARD MIRAJANE.
- ( chuckles )
- YOU CAN'T FIGHT US
IF YOU CAN'T MOVE.
- NICE TRY, THAT SPELL'S
COMPLETELY USELESS
IF I DON'T LOOK
INTO YOUR EYES.
- GOOD THING THAT'S NOT THE ONLY
SPELL I'VE GOT UP MY SLEEVE.
FAIRY MACHINE GUN.
LEPRECHAUN.
- NO, EVERGREEN.
COME ON, MIRA.
DO I HAVE TO FIGHT YOU?
( screaming )
I REALLY DIDN'T WANT IT
TO COME TO THIS.
FULL-BODY TAKE OVER,
BEAST SOUL.
- IT'S OVER NOW.
- NO, WAIT.
- YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO STOP
ME?  I'LL BLOW YOU BOTH AWAY.
- BEFORE YOU DO, THERE'S
SOMETHING YOU SHOULD KNOW.
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- THEY'VE GOT EVERY RIGHT
TO BE COCKY.
THEY COULD BE THE BEST FIGHTERS
IN THE ENTIRE GUILD.
- THOSE TWO DON'T MESS AROUND.
- I'LL SHOW THEM.
I'M DETERMINED TO FOLLOW
IN MY MASTER'S FOOTSTEPS.
I WON'T LET THEM BEAT ME.
COME OUT AND FACE ME RIGHT NOW,
YOU COWARDS.
THEY HERE?
- NO.
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT WE LOST TO THEM.
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- I REALLY WISH I WAS,
BUT NO.
THEY BEAT US AND MOVED ON
WHILE YOU WERE PASSED OUT.
- OH!  HOW COULD I FAIL
THIS YEAR, TOO?
- IT'S MY FAULT.  YOU NEVER
SHOULD'VE TEAMED UP WITH ME.
( sniffles ) I TRIED MY BEST,
BUT IT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
( crying )
- DON'T CRY.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
TRY NOT TO BE SO HARD
ON YOURSELF, OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT. WE MADE IT
THROUGH THE FIRST ROUND, BABY.
- LET'S HOPE THE TOUGHER GUYS
LIKE NATSU AND FRIED
WERE KNOCKED OUT THIS ROUND.
WITH THEM GONE,
IT'LL BE A WALK IN THE PARK.
OH, WAIT.
CANA'S A MAJOR CONTENDER, TOO.
- DON'T BE STUPID, MAN.
YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO,
THERE AIN'T NO EASY WAY
TO BECOME AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
- YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
THE TWO OF US MADE BEATING MEST
LIKE THAT LOOK PRETTY EASY.
- NO KIDDING.  I DON'T REMEMBER
HIM BEING SO WEAK.
HE WAS AT A DISADVANTAGE
'CAUSE OF WENDY,
BUT I FEEL LIKE HE USED
TO BE STRONGER THAN THAT.
- PROBABLY BECAUSE
YOU'VE GOTTEN STRONGER.
- WEIRD.  THIS IS A FIRST.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
IF I FOUGHT HIM BEFORE,
AND I'M THE TYPE
WHO NEVER FORGETS A FIGHT.
- SURE THIS ISN'T A CASE
OF SELECTIVE MEMORY?
LIKE HE KICKED YOUR BUTT AND NOW
YOU DON'T WANNA REMEMBER?
- HMM, LET'S SEE.
MEST MANAGED TO GET PRETTY FAR
IN LAST YEAR'S S-CLASS TRIAL,
DIDN'T HE?
- HE DID,
AS FAR AS I KNOW.
- I THOUGHT SO.
HEY, DO YOU REMEMBER WHO
HIS PARTNER WAS LAST TIME?
- THAT'S WEIRD.
I KEEP DRAWING A BLANK.
- YEAH.  ME TOO,
AND MY MEMORY'S NOT THAT BAD.
- MINE'S NOT EITHER. - I
CAN ONLY PICTURE A FEW THINGS
ABOUT MEST,
AND THEY'RE ALL HAZY.
- IT'S LIKE I TRY TO THINK BACK,
BUT THEN I HIT
SOME KIND OF BLOCK.
I CAN'T SEEM TO REMEMBER
ANYTHING BEFORE IT.
- Both: HMM.
- Lucy: GRAY.  LOKE.
- I KNEW YOU GUYS WOULD HAVE
NO PROBLEM MAKING IT PAST
THE FIRST ROUND.
- NICE WORK.  CONGRATULATIONS.
- I TOLD YOU.  WE WERE LUCKY
TO GET THE "SERENITY" ROUTE.
- LUCKY?  BUT I DIDN'T GET
TO BEAT UP A SINGLE PERSON.
- WOW, WE WERE THE ONLY ONES
WHO WERE ABLE TO CLEAR
THE FIRST ROUND?
- HMM, WHERE'S NATSU?
HE'S SITTING RIGHT OVER THERE.
- HE SEEMS KIND OF DOWN.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
- IT'S A LONG STORY
- ALL RIGHT.
I BELIEVE ALL OUR WINNERS
ARE HERE NOW.
- OH, YEAH.
- WELL, IN THAT CASE,
THESE ARE THE RESULTS THUS FAR.
CANA AND LUCY DEFEATED FRIED
AND BIXLOW IN COMBAT.
NICELY DONE, LADIES.
- THEY BEAT FRIED?  HOW?
- Makarov: NATSU AND HAPPY
SURMOUNTED THE OBSTACLE
KNOWN AS GILDARTS.
GOOD JOB.
- NO WAY.  THOSE TWO?
- YEAH, BUT I DIDN'T REALLY
DO MUCH OF ANYTHING.
- LEVY AND GAJEEL CHOSE
THE "SERENITY" ROUTE.
WELL, AREN'T YOU LUCKY?
- WELL, I THINK IT'S SUCKY.
- GRAY AND LOKE DEFEATED
MEST AND WENDY IN COMBAT.
WAY TO GO, BOYS.
- JUVIA DIDN'T EVEN MAKE IT
THROUGH THE FIRST ROUND?
WHAT'S WITH THE CREEPY LOOK
ON YOUR FACE, GRAMPS?
- UNFORTUNATELY, LUCK WAS NOT
ON JUVIA AND LISANNA'S
SIDE TODAY.
THEIR ROUTE LED
TO "SHE WHO KNOWS NO MERCY."
- OH.
- WANT ANOTHER GO AT ME?
- NO, WE SURRENDER.
- THAT SUCKS.
- ELFMAN AND EVERGREEN
AREN'T HERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HAPPENED TO 'EM?
- WELL,
BY PROCESS OF ELIMINATION,
THE ONLY OTHER ROUTE--
- ( both gasp )
- Both: MIRAJANE!
- I FEEL SORRY FOR THEM.
- I COULD TAKE HER,
BUT THOSE TWO HAD NO CHANCE.
- Elfman:
DON'T COUNT US OUT YET.
DIDN'T THINK WE COULD BEAT
MY BIG SIS, DID YOU?
- GUESS WHO'S MOVING ON
TO ROUND TWO.
- MY WORD. - HOW THE
HECK DID YOU BEAT MIRA?
- UH...
A REAL MAN DOESN'T
BRAG ABOUT HIS WINS.
- LET'S JUST SAY WE TOOK
FULL ADVANTAGE
OF CATCHING HER OFF-GUARD.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- AHEM.  BACK TO THE TRIAL.
AS IT STANDS,
THERE ARE FIVE TEAMS LEFT.
NATSU AND HAPPY,
GRAY AND LOKE,
LEVY AND GAJEEL,
CANA AND LUCY
AND ELFMAN AND EVERGREEN.
CONGRATULATIONS ON PASSING
THE FIRST ROUND.
NOW THAT EVERYONE'S HERE, LET'S
MOVE ON TO THE SECOND ROUND.
- NATSU, I HATE TO SEE YOU
SO DOWN IN THE DUMPS.
- I'M NOT.
I'M JUST DOING SOME THINKING.
- YOU'RE THINKING?
YOU NEVER DO THAT.
BE CAREFUL.
YOU MIGHT HURT YOURSELF.
- JEEZ, HOW LITTLE DO YOU
THINK OF HIM, HAPPY?
- Gildarts:
I'LL TAKE YOU ON AGAIN ANYTIME.
NOW GO BECOME
AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
YOU HEAR ME?
- I'M GONNA DO MY BEST.
YOU'LL SEE.
GRAY.  CANA.
LEVY.  ELFMAN.
ONLY ONE OF US IS GONNA BE
AN S-CLASS WIZARD
AND THAT'S ME.
- YEAH, RIGHT, THERE'S NO WAY
I'M LOSING TO YOU.
- ( laughs )
- NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
- CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.
'CAUSE I'M A REAL MAN, BABY.
- OH, YEAH,
I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW.
- AYE, SIR.
- I'M GONNA DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO MAKE YOU
AN S-CLASS WIZARD, CANA.
- BETTER HOPE YOU DON'T
HAVE TO FIGHT ME.
'CAUSE I WON'T GO EASY ON YOU.
- ( laughs )
BIG TALK FOR A BUNCH OF WIMPS.
- WHAT THE HECK
DID YOU CALL ME? ( winces )
- COME ON, ELFMAN,
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
- WELL, WE KNOW WHO'S
NOT GONNA MAKE S-CLASS.
- LISTEN. I'M ABOUT
TO GIVE INSTRUCTIONS
FOR THE SECOND PART.
THE NEXT STAGE
OF THE S-CLASS TRIAL STARTS NOW.
- ( all gasp )
( all gasp )
- TO PASS THE NEXT ROUND,
YOU MUST SEARCH THE ISLAND
FOR THE GRAVE
OF FAIRY TAIL'S FOUNDER--
MAVIS VERMILLION.
- I FORGOT SHE WAS BURIED HERE.
- AND WE'VE GOTTA FIND
WHERE THAT IS.
- COME ON, GRAMPS.
THAT'S ALMOST TOO EASY.
- NO JOKE.
- YOU HAVE SIX HOURS
TO FIND IT OR YOU FAIL.
NO EXCUSES.
IS THAT CHALLENGING ENOUGH?
VERY WELL.  I'LL BE WAITING
FOR YOU AT MAVIS' GRAVE.
- YOU READY?  LET'S GO!
- AYE, SIR.
- Narrator:
MEANWHILE, WENDY IS STILL AT IT.
- ( crying )
- IF YOU KEEP THAT UP,
YOU'LL RUN OUT OF TEARS.
- I'M SORRY.  I CAN'T STOP.
- LISTEN, WENDY.
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
MAKAROV SAID THIS ISLAND
IS CONSIDERED
FAIRY TAIL'S SACRED GROUND.
SO DO YOU KNOW WHY?
- WELL, YEAH, I THINK SO.
BECAUSE THIS IS WHERE THE
GUILD'S FIRST MASTER IS BURIED.
- YEAH.  ALTHOUGH THAT
CAN'T BE THE ONLY REASON.
TENROU ISLAND'S PROTECTED
BY A POWERFUL FORCE FIELD
THAT HIDES IT FROM OUTSIDERS.
APPARENTLY,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO FIND,
NO MATTER WHAT KIND OF
MAGIC YOU USE.
MAVIS WAS SPECIAL,
BUT I DON'T THINK THEY'D GO TO
SUCH LENGTHS TO HIDE HER GRAVE.
SUPPOSEDLY,
THERE'S A MAJOR SECRET
REGARDING THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
THAT'S HIDDEN SOMEWHERE
ON THIS ISLAND.
- DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THE SECRET IS?
- NOPE.  I HAVE NO IDEA.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DO YOU WANNA GO
AND DO SOME EXPLORING?
- ( giggles )
- THE PRINCE--
I MEAN, MYSTOGAN,
FELT IT WAS BEST TO AVOID
CONTACT WITH PEOPLE
WHENEVER HE VISITED
THIS WORLD.
- I'VE BEEN TOLD HE WOULD
PUT EVERYONE TO SLEEP
WHEN HE DROPPED BY THE GUILD.
I ASSUME HE WAS TRYING
TO PREVENT THEM
FROM SEEING HIS FACE.
- AND THAT'S WHY I FIND
IT HARD TO BELIEVE
HE'D HAVE A PUPIL HERE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
- WHILE IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN BASELESS SPECULATION,
I HAVE A THEORY.
- IT'S SO PRETTY UP HERE.
- BE CAREFUL.
- ( giggles )
- I KNOW IT MIGHT SOUND CRAZY,
BUT I'M NOT SURE MEST IS
A MEMBER OF FAIRY TAIL.
- ( panting )
PLEASE DON'T EAT ME!
- ( roaring )
- PICK UP THE PACE, LUCY.
- ( screaming )
PRETTY PLEASE WITH SUGAR ON TOP.
NO, I'M TOO CUTE TO DIE!
- MAN, I HATE THIS ISLAND.
- I'M STARTING TO THINK
I MIGHT DIE HERE.
- THIS AIN'T NOTHING BUT A BUMP
ON THE ROAD
ON MY WAY TO BEING S-CLASS.
- SURE, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- FOLLOW A REAL MAN TO SAFETY!
- OH, SHUT UP.
YOU'RE NOT THE BOSS OF ME.
- STOP INTERRUPTING ME
OR YOU'RE GONNA GET CHARRED.
- ( roaring )
- I WARNED YOU.
- THERE'S NO STOPPING NATSU
WHEN HE WANTS SOMETHING,
AND HE WANTS
TO FINISH THIS TEST.
- ( groans )
- ( sighs )
- HOORAY!  WAY TO GO, NATSU.
YOU READY TO GET MOVING?
- NO, NOT YET.
GIVE ME A SEC.
- YOU'D BETTER TELL ME WHERE THE
FIRST GUILD MASTER'S GRAVE IS,
OR I'M GONNA BURN YOU TO
A CRISP, YOU GOT THAT, BIG GUY?
- THAT'S CUCKOO!
- I DON'T KNOW.
- THAT'S COOL.
- IT ANSWERED YOU?
- HOW DOES GRAMPS EXPECT US
TO FIND MAVIS' GRAVE
WHEN HE DIDN'T EVEN BOTHER
TO GIVE US ANY CLUES?
- PRETTY SNEAKY.
I GUESS THIS ROUND'S GONNA BE
HARDER THAN WE THOUGHT.
- YOU KNOW,
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
THIS ISLAND'S SHAPED
KIND OF FUNKY, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, SO?
- YOU WANNA GO SEE WHAT'S
AT THE TOP WITH ME?
- DEFINITELY!
- AWESOME!
I KNEW TEAMING UP WITH YOU
WAS A GOOD IDEA.
I COULDN'T DO THIS WITHOUT
YOU, LITTLE BUDDY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY TO HEAD TO THE TOP?
- YEP, YOU KNOW IT.
- Narrator: THIS IS FAIRY TAIL'S
MAKESHIFT BASE ON TENROU ISLAND.
- NO WAY.  ELFMAN AND EVERGREEN
SAID THEY'RE GETTING MARRIED?
- YEP, IT TOTALLY CAUGHT ME OFF
GUARD AND THAT GAVE THEM
AN OPENING TO ATTACK.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
THEY'VE OBVIOUSLY BEEN DATING
AWHILE IF THEY'RE
GETTING MARRIED,
BUT YOU NEVER MENTIONED IT.
- I THINK THEY JUST WANTED
TO SAY SOMETHING SHOCKING
TO THROW ME OFF.  I GUESS I'VE
STILL GOT A LOT TO LEARN.
- WHAT IF IT WASN'T A STRATEGY?
- REMEMBER WHO WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT HERE.
KNOWING MY BROTHER,
I DOUBT THAT IT'S TRUE.
I NEVER IMAGINED
THE TWO OF THEM
GETTING MARRIED
AND HAVING BABIES.
HMM.
- I'M A REAL BABY.
- ( crying )
- THERE'S NO NEED TO CRY.
IT'S KIND OF CUTE,
DEPENDING ON HOW YOU LOOK AT IT.
- Lisanna: YOU KNOW,
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
THEY'D MAKE AN AWESOME COUPLE.
- THEY'RE GONNA HAVE BABIES.
- HEY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO FRIED AND BIXLOW?
- APPARENTLY, THE TWO OF THEM
AND GILDARTS WENT BACK HOME.
- JEEZ.
TALK ABOUT IMPATIENT.
THEY COULD'VE STAYED AND WATCHED
THE REST OF THE TRIAL.
- I'M MORE CONCERNED ABOUT MEST
AND WENDY.  WHERE ARE THEY?
- THEY SHOULD'VE
BEEN HERE BY NOW.
- THEY PROBABLY JUST FORGOT THAT
WE'RE ALL SUPPOSED TO MEET HERE.
- BABIES.  BABIES.
- SO THIS MEST GUY.
- I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT HIM
'CAUSE I NEVER RAN
INTO HIS COUNTERPART IN EDOLAS.
DID HE JOIN FAIRY TAIL DURING
THE TWO YEARS THAT I WAS GONE?
- I DON'T KNOW, DID HE?
- I FEEL LIKE HE'S ALWAYS
BEEN A MEMBER.
- HE DOESN'T MAKE
A BIG IMPRESSION, HUH?
- I VOLUNTEER TO GO
AND LOOK FOR THEM.
I'M STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE WORRIED.
- YOU TWO STAY HERE
AND GUARD THE TENT.
I'M GOING TO ACCOMPANY
JUVIA ON HER SEARCH.
- I WANTED TO DITCH THEM AND GO
CHEER ON MY BELOVED GRAY.
- ( screaming )
- A REAL MAN SHOULD NEVER
RUN FROM HIS ENEMY.
- IF YOU DON'T STOP THIS
"REAL MAN" NONSENSE,
I'LL FINISH YOU MYSELF.
- LOOK OUT!
- ( groaning )
- OW, THAT HURT.
- HEY!  WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
DON'T YOU DARE START THINKING
I'M INTERESTED IN YOU
JUST BECAUSE
OF WHAT I SAID TO MIRA.
I WAS ONLY TRYING TO
THROW HER OFF HER GAME,
NOT EXPRESSING ANY REAL DESIRE
TO HOOK UP WITH YOU, BONEHEAD.
- WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU, THOUGH,
THAT WAS PRETTY SMOOTH.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE A NICE GIRL
LIKE YOU CAME UP
WITH SUCH
A NAUGHTY TRICK.
- YOU MAKE IT SOUND SO DIRTY.
- HUH?  PEOPLE?
I'M CONFUSED.
WHY HAVE YOU COME TO
SUCH A DESOLATE PLACE?
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION THAT
THIS ISLAND WAS UNINHABITED.
- WELL, YOU WERE WRONG, PAL.
- YOU'RE TRESPASSING.
ONLY MEMBERS OF OUR GUILD
ARE ALLOWED HERE.
- I'M TRESPASSING?
FORGIVE ME.
I DIDN'T KNOW THIS ISLAND
WAS CONTROLLED BY A GUILD.
- IT IS.  OURS!
- NO, STAY BACK!
IF YOU VALUE YOUR LIFE,
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER TO ME.
- THAT KIND OF SOUNDS
LIKE A CHALLENGE.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT YOU.
I'LL LEAVE THE ISLAND
PEACEFULLY.
PLEASE JUST DON'T COME NEAR ME.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT HE SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
- NO.  HERE IT COMES.
PREDATORY DEATH.
I CAN'T STOP IT.
( grunting )
- Natsu: GET DOWN!
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
YOU.
NATSU.
- WHO ARE YOU?
YOU'D BETTER ANSWER ME
OR ELSE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: I KNOW THIS
IS A WEIRD TIME TO ASK,
BUT IF YOU'RE A CAT,
WHY ARE YOU BLUE?
- Happy:
YEAH, IT IS A WEIRD TIME TO ASK.
I DON'T KNOW, NATSU.
I DON'T REALLY THINK
THERE IS A REASON.
- Natsu:
THERE'S GOT TO BE.
SOMEONE ONCE SAID, "EVERYTHING
HAPPENS FOR A REASON."
I MEAN, IT WAS AN OLD GUY
WALKING DOWN THE STREET,
BUT YOU GET THE POINT.
- Happy: YOU LEARNED THAT
FROM SOME RANDOM OLD GUY?
MAN, I THOUGHT YOU FINALLY
PICKED UP A BOOK.
- Happy and Natsu:
NEXT TIME, "BLACK WIZARD"!
- Happy: MAYBE IT'S 'CAUSE I'M
LIKE THE BLUEBIRD OF HAPPINESS.
THAT'S HOW I GOT MY NAME.
REMEMBER?
PLUS I HAVE WINGS
AND I CAN FLY.
- Natsu: YOU SOUND MORE
LIKE A BIRD THAN A CAT.