- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Happy: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
AFTER ALL OF OUR HARD WORK,
WE FINALLY BEAT BRAIN,
THE LEADER
OF THE ORACION SEIS.
- Gray: WHAT'S THIS "WE" STUFF?
POPS TOOK HIM OUT SOLO.
- Lucy: CAN WE FOCUS
ON WHAT'S IMPORTANT HERE,
LIKE WHY NIRVANA
IS STILL MOVING?
HOW DO WE TO STOP THIS THING?
- Erza: AS LONG AS WE
DRAW BREATH INTO OUR LUNGS,
WE SHALL KEEP HOPE ALIVE
INSIDE OUR HEARTS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
THE BELOVED MAGICAL GUILD
THAT COALITION MEMBERS WENDY,
MARVELL AND CARLA CALL HOME--
CAIT SHELTER.
- ( all chattering )
- I'VE GOT TERRIBLE NEWS,
EVERYBODY.
NIRVANA'S BEEN ACTIVATED.
IT'S HEADING STRAIGHT FOR US!
- SERIOUSLY?
- NOT EVEN THE COALITION
COULD STOP THAT MONSTROSITY?
- HOW COULD THEY FAIL WITH BOTH
ERZA AND JURA ON THEIR SIDE?
- MASTER?
- NABURA.
- ( all clamoring )
- WHY POUR A GLASS IF YOU'RE
GONNA CHUG FROM THE BOTTLE?
- NABURA.
- PLEASE TELL US, SIR.
NIRVANA WILL BE HERE
ANY MINUTE!
- DON'T TELL ME THAT INFERNAL
THING IS HEADED OUR WAY?!
- Man: WOULD YOU PLEASE SWALLOW
BEFORE YOU SPEAK, MASTER?
- NIRVANA HAS SET
ITS WAKING EYES UPON US.
COULD THIS BE OUR FATE
OR NOTHING MORE
THAN COINCIDENCE, NABURA?
- IF THE COALITION FAILED,
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED TO
WENDY? - DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE THE ANSWER
TO THAT QUESTION
WOULD SIT WELL WITH ANY OF US.
- ( chugging )
DO NOT BURDEN YOURSELVES
WITH WORRY.
- All: DRINK OR TALK!
- FEAR NOT!
THE MAGIC OF LIGHT
IS ALIVE AND WELL.
YES, NABURA!
ITS INCANDESCENT GLOW
SHALL LEAD US TO VICTORY.
- YEAH!
- STILL THIS DOESN'T FEEL
LIKE A COINCIDENCE, DOES IT?
- AT THIS POINT,
IT'S FAIRLY OBVIOUS
SOMEONE'S FIGURED OUT
WHO WE ARE.
- Woman: THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE COMING FOR US.
- PLEASE GUIDE US, NABURA.
- AS LONG AS I'VE KNOWN YOU,
I STILL HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT "NABURA" EVEN MEANS.
- Man: SHOULDN'T WE BE
EVACUATING, MASTER?
WE CAN'T CONJURE A BARRIER
STRONG ENOUGH STOP NIRVANA.
- YOU FOOLS!
- ( all gasping )
- HAVE YOU ALL FORGOTTEN,
NABURA, THERE ARE WIZARDS
FIGHTING TO STOP
ITS DESTRUCTIVE ADVANCE?
WE MUST HAVE FAITH
THAT THEY'LL SUCCEED,
AND NOT DISHONOR THEM
BY RUNNING AWAY.
TRUST ME, I KNOW.
IT'S HARD TO KEEP FAITH
IN THE GRIP OF FEAR.
PERHAPS THE TIME
HAS FINALLY COME.
WE KNEW OUR TRANSGRESSIONS
WOULD CATCH UP TO US ONE DAY.
- Happy: "YOUR WORDS"!
- SO IF THERE ISN'T A PILOT SEAT
OR CONTROL PANEL
WHERE WE CAN STOP THIS THING,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- DESTROY IT, OF COURSE.
- LEAVE IT TO US
TO DEMOLISH A CITY, RIGHT?
- NOT TO SOUND PESSIMISTIC,
BUT THAT'S A PRETTY TALL ORDER.
- BEFORE THAT,
WE SHOULD SEE IF BRAIN KNOWS
HOW TO STOP NIRVANA.
- I DOUBT THAT BRUTE WOULD SHARE
SUCH INFORMATION WITH US.
- IF HE WON'T TELL US,
MAYBE JELLAL WILL KNOW.
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- THINK OF SOMETHING
THAT'LL HELP?
- WELL, I'M NOT QUITE SURE,
BUT IT MAY BE THE BEST OPTION
WE HAVE,
SO I'LL DO MY BEST
TO FIND IT.
- WENDY?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, CHILD?
- HEY!
- SHE SURE IS DETERMINED.
- Hoteye: MY FRIENDS,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
IT IS I,
THE WIZARD KNOWN AS HOTEYE.
- YOU GUYS HEAR THAT TOO
OR AM I GOIN' CRAZY?
- I HEARD IT. - DID YOU
DEFEAT MIDNIGHT, RICHARD?
- I TRIED MY BEST,
BUT IN THE END,
IT SEEMS MY MAGIC SIMPLY WASN'T
STRONG ENOUGH TO TRUMP HIS.
DO NOT CONCERN YOURSELF
WITH MY RESCUE.
YOU MUST WORK TOGETHER TO
BRING MIDNIGHT DOWN FOR GOOD.
IF YOU SUCCEED
IN DEFEATING HIM,
NIRVANA'S SOURCE OF MAGIC POWER
WILL BE RENDERED DRY
AND THE CITY WILL CEASE
ITS DESTRUCTIVE PATH.
- AM I SUPPOSED
TO KNOW THIS GUY?
- SO WE CAN STOP NIRVANA WITHOUT
DESTROYING THE WHOLE THING?
- ( whimpering )
- HE'S DIRECTLY BELOW YOU,
JUST OUTSIDE
OF THE ROYAL THRONE.
HIS POWER IS NOT ONE
TO BE UNDERESTIMATED.
PLEASE, BE CAUTIOUS,
MY FRIENDS.
- THE SAME TO YOU, RICHARD.
- WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
- NICE.
THIS MESS
JUST GOT A WHOLE LOT EASIER.
- I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW.
WE'RE COMIN' FOR YOU,
SLEEPY HEAD.
- COME ON.  I KNOW YOU
CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT.
- Natsu: ALL RIGHT,
HOW ABOUT SIR SNORES-A-LOT?
- Hoteye:
ONLY ONE OF THE SIX PRAYERS
STILL REMAINS
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
EVERY OUNCE OF MY TRUST AND
CONFIDENCE
BELONGS TO YOU, MY FRIENDS.
DEFEAT MIDNIGHT, AND STOP
NIRVANA ONCE AND FOR ALL.
OH YEAH!
( disguised voice ) I WISH YOU
LUCK, MY FAITHFUL COMRADES.
( grunting )
- Jura: SIR RICHARD!
- ( chuckling )
YOU MAY HAVE BESTED ME,
BUT IT WILL COME AT A PRICE.
- HE SHOULD BE THROUGH THERE.
- LET'S DO THIS THING!
( grunting )
ALL RIGHT, FREAK.
TIME FOR A DIRT NAP!
- ( all gasping )
- EVERYBODY GET DOWN!
- WHAT WAS THAT EXPLOSION?
- IT WAS NEAR THE THRONE.
- FATHER CAN BE
SO SELFISH SOMETIMES.
HE TOOK A BIG BITE
OUT OF MY FUN
AND LEFT ME
WITH MEASLY SCRAPS.
NOW SINCE YOU'RE THE LAST
OF MY PREY,
AT LEAST MAKE IT
ENTERTAINING FOR ME.
- STAND BACK.
HE'S MINE.
- JELLAL, YOU CAN'T.
- HEY, YOU GUYS,
EVERYONE OKAY?
- KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN,
WILL YA?
I'M TRYING TO SLEEP HERE.
- AYE.
- ARE WE REALLY THIS STUPID?
WE'RE IN FAIRY TAIL.
I CAN'T ACCEPT THAT WE FELL
FOR THAT TRAP SO EASILY.
- WELL, WE'RE ALSO DUMB ENOUGH
TO GET BURIED ALIVE.
- WHAT?  BUT IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN WHERE'S JURA?
- ( grunts )
- ( panting )
- NO!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- HE RISKED HIS LIFE
TO PROTECT US.
- POPS, HANG IN THERE!
- THE STRENGTH AND COURAGE
YOU POSSESS--
YOUR GUILD IS A LUCKY ONE.
IT BRINGS ME GREAT RELIEF
TO KNOW YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
- POPS, NO!
- YOU CAN'T GO LIKE THIS!
- PLEASE, DON'T DIE!
- Natsu: JURA!
- WE GOTTA FIND HIM
BEFORE THIS THING
GETS ANY CLOSER TO CAIT SHELTER.
- IF WE DON'T LAND SHORTLY,
CHILD,
I'M LIABLE TO LOSE MY GRIP
ON YOU FOR GOOD.
- OH, I'M SORRY,
I WASN'T PAYING ATTENTION.
LET'S CONTINUE THE SEARCH
ON FOOT.  SOUND GOOD?
- YOUR SENSE OF SMELL
WILL BE OUR GUIDE.
- ( both sigh )
- HONESTLY, I'M KIND OF NERVOUS
ABOUT FINDING HIM
'CAUSE I'VE NOTICED
HE HAS A DIFFERENT SCENT
THAN THE ONE I REMEMBER
FROM BEFORE.
- WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T
LET THAT DISTRACT YOU
FROM COMPLETING OUR GOAL.
IF WE CAN FIND HIM,
WE MAY BE ABLE
TO STOP NIRVANA FROM MOVING.
- Wendy: WHEREVER YOU ARE,
JELLAL, PLEASE BE SAFE.
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
ABOUT ME, BUT I DON'T CARE.
JUST KNOW, I'VE NEVER ONCE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN A PART OF MY
THOUGHTS EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- HOW COULD I MISS HIM
AT SUCH CLOSE RANGE?
- ( chuckles )
- PLEASE STOP THIS
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE IN NO CONDITION
TO FIGHT HIM.  LET ME DO IT.
- WELL?
I'M WAITING.
- ( grunts )
- THIS IS BORING.
YOU'RE THE FEARSOME JELLAL
I KEEP HEARING ABOUT?
TALK ABOUT A WASTE OF TIME.
- Midnight:
DID YOU LOSE YOUR MEMORY
AND FORGET
HOW TO USE MAGIC TOO?
HOW PATHETIC.
- Erza: MEMORIES OR NO,
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE
GONE DOWN SO QUICKLY.
- ( chuckles )
AT LEAST YOU'RE DETERMINED.
- THE SELF-DESTRUCTION CIRCLE
HE PLACED ON HIMSELF
MUST'VE DRAINED MORE OF HIS
MAGIC ENERGY THAN HE THOUGHT.
- WHAT A NICE SURPRISE.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO SEEING
JUST HOW MUCH PAIN
YOU CAN ENDURE.
- IF ERZA SCARLET'S THAT EAGER
TO HAVE HER TURN,
WHO AM I TO KEEP HER WAITING?
- Erza: MY SWORD
DIDN'T EVEN HIT HIM!
- NO, YOU MUSTN'T
TAKE YOUR CHANCES AGAINST HIM.
HE'S TOO DANGEROUS.
- HOW IS HE DOING THAT?
WHAT IS THIS? AH!
- LET HER GO.
- AAH!
NOW I GET IT.
YOU USE REFLECTOR MAGIC.
- YES.
AND WHATEVER KIND OF ATTACK
YOU THROW AT ME,
I'LL BE ABLE TO TWIST
AND MANIPULATE ALL OF IT.
BESIDES GIVING ME
A FLAWLESS DEFENSE,
MY MAGIC ALLOWS ME
TO DOMINATE MY OPPONENTS.
EVEN LIGHT ITSELF
BENDS TO MY WILL.
- COULD SUCH A POWER
TRULY EXIST?
- EVERY OPPONENT
HAS THEIR FLAWS.
YOU ARE NO DIFFERENT.
I WILL BE YOUR END!
- THAT'S IT--
RUSH TOWARDS YOUR DOOM.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOUR FACE
AS I TWIST YOUR BODY APART.
- OH, MAN,
HE LOOKS BAD.
- HANG IN THERE, POPS.
WE'LL GET HELP FOR YA.
- Happy:
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- Klodoa: RIDICULOUS.
BRAIN IS SUCH A FOOL.
HE USED THE LAST OF HIS POWER
TO LAY HIS TRAP,
YET ONLY ONE OF YOU
FELL IN ITS SNARE.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- OVER THERE!
- HE WAS A PITIFUL LEADER,
A DISGRACE TO THE SIX DEMONS.
BUT OUR GOAL
HAS NOT FALLEN OUT OF REACH.
AS LONG AS MIDNIGHT STANDS,
WE SHALL BE VICTORIOUS.
SINCE HE'S BUSY AT THE MOMENT,
THERE'S NOTHING KEEPING ME
FROM DISPOSING OF YOU MYSELF.
- THAT CANE'S TALKIN' TO ME!
- AS A TALKING CAT,
I WOULDN'T THINK YOU'D FIND IT
ALL THAT SURPRISING.
- I GUESS.
- ( chuckling )
( guffawing )
- THAT'S CRAZY.
IT'S THE STAFF THAT BRAIN
WAS CARRYING AROUND.
- 'KAY, I'M FREAKED OUT NOW.
- OH, WOULD YOU KNOCK OFF
THE CREEPY LAUGHING?
I'VE ALREADY GOT A SPLITTING
HEADACHE THANKS TO YOUR BOSS--
- HEY!
DON'T GO GRABBING THAT.
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHERE IT'S BEEN, YOU KNOW?
- STOP THIS CITY RIGHT NOW,
YOU PIECE OF ROTTING DRIFTWOOD.
- HOW DARE YOU
INSULT MY FAMILY LEGACY?
I COME FROM A LONG LINE
OF PROUD CEDAR,
SO SHOW SOME RESPECT.
BEFORE YOU
IS THE VENERATED SEVENTH MEMBER
OF THE ORACION SEIS,
EMERGED FROM HIS SLUMBER
TO DESTROY YOU ALL--
- I'VE HEARD JUST
ABOUT ENOUGH OUTTA YOU!
- LET GO OF ME THIS INSTANT!
- HOLD ON, I THOUGHT
THERE WERE ONLY SIX MEMBERS
OF THE ORACION SEIS.
- PROFESSOR HAPPY'S BACK WITH
ANOTHER CLASS
ABOUT "FAIRY TAIL."
- LUCY'S RIGHT,
FOR A CHANGE.
THE WORD IN "SEIS"
IN ORACION SEIS MEANS SIX,
AS IN THERE ARE SIX MEMBERS
THAT MAKE UP THE GUILD.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- I KNOW, AND DON'T THINK
I DIDN'T CATCH YOU SLIPPING
IN THAT "FOR A CHANGE" COMMENT,
YA FLEABAG.
- WHO CARES? WHATEVER THE
NUMBER OF MEMBERS MIGHT BE,
A CANE IS TALKING
ABOUT KICKING OUR BUTTS.
- LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE--
IT CAN'T REALLY KICK OUR BUTTS
SINCE IT HAS NO FEET.
- AH!
UNCIVILIZED NEANDERTHAL.
IT WON'T BE LONG UNTIL THEIR
WRETCHED GUILD
IS WITHIN OUR SIGHTS.
THEN WE CAN FINALLY BEGIN TO
CLEANSE THIS WORLD OF REFUSE.
- YOU MEAN WE'RE ALREADY
THAT CLOSE TO CAIT SHELTER?
- INDEED WE ARE!
ONCE THEY'RE STAMPED OUT,
WE CAN TRULY BEGIN
OUR CRUSADE OF DARKNESS.
( cackling )
- NOW, DANCE, MY SWORDS!
- YOU COULD THROW A THOUSAND,
BUT THEY STILL WON'T HIT ME.
SO TELL ME,
HOW'S IT FEEL TO FEND OFF
ONE OF YOUR OWN ATTACKS?
- GET OUT OF THERE!
- THAT'S BETTER.
NOW SOOTHE ME WITH A LULLABY
OF TORMENT AND AGONY.
- AAH!
- ( laughs )
NOTHING WHETS MY APPETITE
LIKE TORTURED SCREAMS.
IMPRESSIVE...
BUT FUTILE.
SPIRAL PAIN!
- ( screams )
- NO, ERZA.
- FINISHED ALREADY?
- CURSE YOU.
- YOU CAN'T DIE ON ME YET.
I STILL WANT TO PLAY.
I NEED ENTERTAINMENT.
AT LEAST
UNTIL WE REACH CAIT SHELTER.
- WHAT IS THIS CAIT SHELTER?
- IT'S OUR FIRST TARGET,
OF COURSE.
- WHAT EARNED THEM THAT HONOR?
- AN EXCELLENT QUESTION.
LONG AGO, A PEACEFUL TRIBE,
THE NIRVITS,
CREATED NIRVANA,
HOPING TO END
A CATACLYSMIC WAR.
BUT THE TOOL THEY'D CREATED
WAS FAR MORE DANGEROUS
THAN THE WAR
THEY SOUGHT TO END.
SO THEY SEALED IT AWAY,
HOPING IT WOULD NEVER
BE USED AGAIN.
THEY WERE SO AFRAID OF IT,
THEY SWORE TO KEEP WATCH
OVER THE BURIAL SITE.
THEIR DESCENDANTS HAVE TAKEN UP
THAT TASK THROUGH THE AGES.
AND THEY MAKE UP A GUILD
THAT STILL REMAINS TODAY--
CAIT SHELTER.
- THEY ARE THE ONLY PEOPLE
IN ALL OF EXISTENCE
WITH THE POWER
TO SEAL NIRVANA ONCE MORE.
THEREFORE,
THE NIRVIT BLOODLINE MUST END.
- YOU'D HAVE TO BE INSANE
TO LET AN INCREDIBLE POWER
LIKE THIS TO GO WASTE.
WE WILL UTILIZE IT.
WE WILL SEND THE WORLD SCREAMING
DOWN THE PATH TO SWEET CHAOS.
AND WE'LL START BY MAKING
CAIT SHELTER AN EXAMPLE.
THE NIRVITS
WANTED TO STAY NEUTRAL?
WE'LL FORCE THEM
INTO BLOODY WAR.
NIRVANA WILL TURN THEIR HEARTS
INTO THE BLACKEST
PITCH IMAGINABLE.
AND THEN THEY'LL SLAUGHTER
EACH OTHER!
OH,
WHAT A LULLABY IT'LL BE.
- HEARTLESS MONSTER.
- DO ME A SOLID AND DROP
THE GOODY-GOODY ACT ALREADY.
IT'S KIND OF A DRAG.
AFTER ALL,
YOUR HEART'S SO BLACK,
MINE SHINES NEXT TO YOURS.
ONE COULD SAY
THAT YOU'RE THE VERY EMBODIMENT
OF DARKNESS.
- THAT'S A LIE!
- BE PROUD OF YOURSELF.
YOU FORCED CHILDREN
INTO SLAVE LABOR,
MURDERED YOUR CLOSEST FRIEND,
AND EVEN TRIED TO KILL
SWEET ERZA IN YOUR MAD RISE
FOR THE GREATEST POWER
IN EXISTENCE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MANY INNOCENT PEOPLE
YOU'VE BROUGHT SORROW UPON?
THEY'VE ALL FEARED YOU,
TREMBLED AT YOUR NAME.
AN ENTIRE OCEAN OF TEARS
WAS SHED
FROM THE SUFFERING YOU CAUSED.
YOU INSPIRE ME.
- I WHAT?
- SO WHY DON'T YOU JOIN US?
YOU ARE DESTINED
TO BECOME THE NEWEST MEMBER
OF THE ORACION SEIS.
- DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
THE LIGHT INSIDE YOU
IS BRIGHTER THAN EVER BEFORE.
- ERZA.
- WOW.
I'M SURPRISED YOU CAN STAND.
- AND THAT HOPE WILL GUIDE YOU
THROUGH THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
- YOUR WORDS ARE THE LIGHT
THAT GIVES ME HOPE
AND COURAGE.
- I GET MY REAL FIGHT
AFTER ALL.  WONDERFUL.
DESTROYING YOU
WILL BE A TREAT.
- I SWEAR ON THIS SACRED BLADE
I WIELD,
I WILL END THIS CHAOS
AND YOUR LIFE.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: OF COURSE, THE
STRONGEST GUY OF ALL SHOWS UP
AFTER WE'VE
BEEN BEAT DOWN A BUNCH.
IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE BACK
TO SQUARE ONE AGAIN.
I'M STARTING TO SEE
A PATTERN HERE.
- Natsu: HEY, OUR EARLIER FIGHTS
WEREN'T FOR NOTHIN', RIGHT?
AND LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE--
HE'S THE LAST ONE
WE GOTTA KNOCK DOWN.
SO LET'S FINISH THIS THING.
- MUST BE NICE TO LIVE
SUCH A CAREFREE LIFE, HUH?
I PREFER TO CALL IT
BEING POSITIVE.
- Both: NEXT TIME-- "ZERO"!
- Happy: WOW, I FEEL ALL
INSPIRED NOW. THANKS, NATSU.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
GUESS I'VE GOT PHILANTHROPY
IN MY BLOOD, HUH, LITTLE BUDDY?
- YOU MEAN PHILOSOPHY.