♪
[SOLDIERS chuckle]
You make me sick...
The country's in a state
of emergency and you're
just gettin'
stinkin' drunk?
[MALE SOLDIER B] What
do you expect from Gryder?
He's got a reputation
to uphold...
the biggest
boozehound in town.
Man, he's got it
easy doesn't he?
Gettin' tanked to the
gills while we're out there
risking our lives for justice.
[DORANBOLT] Justice?
You heard him!
The Oración Seis are
back and we're fighting
with all we've got
to try and stop them.
We're working hard
to save the lives
of citizens every
single day.
You have a sense
of right and wrong,
or did you drink
it all away?
I don't wanna
hear about it!
So leave me alone!
What's wrong
with you?!
You made a big
mistake by attacking
a Fiore soldier!
[LAHAR] You've gotten
rusty, Doranbolt.
You can't win.
So stop this.
My name is Mest.
The legendary traitor,
Mest Gryder.
You still insist
on using that name?
No matter,
we need to talk.
Come with me.
[LAHAR] So now you're
at odds with justice?
What happened to you?
[DORANBOLT] To me?
Or to them? To Wendy...
I abandoned them...
Like a coward.
Would you call
that justice?
You can't
change the past,
but the future's
a different story.
Listen... I didn't come
all this way to catch up.
Fiore needs your help.
Yeah, real funny.
I'm being deadly
serious, Doranbolt.
I'm begging you to
help me... Will you do it?
Let's get one thing straight...
I don't answer
to the name Doranbolt.
I'm Mest.
Well, Mest. Why don't
you sober up... Okay?
[HAPPY] Dissonance of Battle!
[JACKPOT laughs]
[ELFMAN] I don't know
what you are, ya freak...
but you sure as
hell ain't a man!
I'll just have to deal
with you later...
Hear me, Octo geezer?!
Watch out! I've got
a big surprise for
a cocky little guy like you!
Oh yeah?!
Looky here! Cool down...
with a Magic Ice Pop!
[ELFMAN] I can't see!
Punch him, not me!
Crap! Sorry, bro.
We can't beat
him like this!
We have to start working
together to take this guy down
with some serious teamwork.
Yeah!
'Kay, let's
do it!
Cancer, will you
lend us a hand?
I'm on it, baby!
Manly charge!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon
Wing Attack!
[JACKPOT] Oh yeah!
I'm gettin' lucky today...!
I hit the Steel Walls!
[NATSU roars]
[ELFMAN] Watch it, Natsu!
[CANCER] Are you tryin'
to boil me in here?!
That went wrong.
[NATSU] It's not my fault!
You keep on lookin'
at me like that and
I'm gonna give you
a taste of my fist!
Hey relax baby. I just
wanna cut your hair.
[arguing]
[LUCY] Would you guys please
stop fighting each other?!
They don't seem like
a good match to me.
I know... But Cana
used her powers
to create these teams. They're
supposed to work well together
and be perfect for
their destinations.
She's usually right on
about these kinda things.
[MAX] So this is what
teamwork feels like?
Come on! Slow down!
My feet are killing me!
[MAX] Maybe you shouldn't
have worn high heels
for mountain climbing.
[EVERGREEN] Sorry Max but
I am a fairy, after all!
[MAX] What the heck
does that mean?
[EVERGREEN]
Owie, owie, owie.
[ERZA] Just be
quiet and walk.
[EVERGREEN] Please,
forgive me queen Erza!
I thought I might get a wee bit
of sympathy from my teammates,
but obviously, my
pain just annoys you!
You seem to have
plenty of energy.
Instead of wasting it
on a hissy-fit,
how about you
just keep moving?
[EVERGREEN] Well, I never!
She just doesn't understand
the concept of being
strong and ladylike.
What was that?
Say it again.
[EVERGREEN]
Oh, nevermind.
Aw, man... This trip
sucks big time.
Why'd I have to be on a team
with these two harpies?
[sneeze]
[CANA] I guess that means
I must be gettin' a lot
of compliments today.
Ya think? Cuz I
wouldn't be so sure.
[CANA gasps]
[CANA] Whaddaya mean by that?!
[JACKPOT] Come on!
Let's get lucky! Yes!
Looks like we got
a lightning bonus!
Oh no, Lucy
are you okay?!
Not really. But I
suppose it could've
been a whole lot worse.
Want more? You haven't
seen how brutal
my Slot magic can get!
Keep up this losing streak
and you'll find out!
C'mon, let's play some more...!
I can't wait to see just how
rotten your luck can get!
[grunts]
I'm gettin'
sick of you!
We have to figure
out a plan of attack.
Got any ideas?
Hell yeah, I do;
and a great one!
It's my trusty standby.
[BOTH] We kick his butt!
[JACKPOT] Whoa! Another
winner! Shaggy Pool!
Now this is what I was
born to do, baby!
[CANCER]
♪ Buh-da-da-da-da... ♪ Cancer!
[BOTH] Would ya please
stop jokin' around?!
My bad... couldn't
help myself.
[laughs]
That sucked...
Teamwork is important,
but I'm afraid
that right now...
Every cat
for themselves!
Well, In my opinion,
there's nothing wrong with
each of us being
a little different.
I couldn't agree
with you more!
I think fish are yummy... you
love to drink Darjeeling Tea...
and Lily likes... Kiwis?
Leave the peel on for a
trip to flavor country!
I don't believe they're
meant to be eaten that way.
The tartness plus the
sweetness make for the
perfect flavor combination!
And the texture of the peel!
I can't get enough of them!
Aren't the peels
kinda... hairy?
Hold on... Does anybody
smell something strange?
[SAMUEL] There's only
one choice for me...
Mushrooms sautéed
in butter sauce.
[PANTHERLILY]
It's Sammy!
[SAMUEL] Greetings,
Brother...
And hello to you,
Happy and Carla.
[JACKPOT laughs]
[JACKPOT] Silly kids,
this game's for grown ups!
[ELFMAN] He's doin' it again!
It's raining. That
gives me an idea!
Open... Gate
of the Water Bearer!
Aquarius!
[AQUARIUS] You'd better have
a good reason for this!
[AQUARIUS] And how many times
do I have to tell you not to
pull me outta some mud--
filled hole in the ground?!
Because I really
don't like it!
Yeah, I'm sorry
about that.
But if you're looking
to blame someone,
it's that creepy
robot-teddy bear's fault!
[AQUARIUS] Why is it
every time I'm on a date,
you have some crisis
you can't handle?
Jealous much?
[LUCY] Gimme
a break.
Well, since I'm here...
Let's get this over with!
Manly attack!
No way, ya meathead!
I'm gettin' to him first!
[JACKPOT] Round-and-round we go!
[NATSU screams]
Huh?!
[AQUARIUS screams]
[crash]
Don't those idiots know
that the house always wins?
You got in my way.
Nuh-uh, you
got in my way.
Will both of you
just shut up?!
Now this is just
getting embarrassing.
The two of them can't seem
to work together at all.
[KATJA] I'm afraid
we're getting to the end...
[squeak]
[KATJA] Hey, Nico...
How much longer do you think
this tree is going to live?
[squeak]
[MALE PRIEST B]
Miss Katja!
What in the world are
you doing out here?!
[KATJA] I was just
looking at this tree.
[squeak]
[MALE PRIEST B] It's
far too dangerous for you
to be outside
on your own like this!
Haven't you heard
about what's going on?!
[KATJA] Of course I've heard...
I know there are not many left.
[MALE PRIEST B]
That's true, so...
That's why
I came out here.
In the hopes that this
tree might remember me...
Just a hope.
[squeak]
[MALE PRIEST B] Miss Katja,
I'm sorry to tell you
that Fabrizio was
discovered and taken away.
[KATJA] He was? Then it's very
likely that I will be next.
If you get too scared,
you can always run away... Okay?
[sad squeak]
[GAJEEL] So is it really that
bad, bein' partnered up with me?
No, It's not
about you, Gajeel.
Cuz if you wanna team up
with that naked freak show,
be my guest.
It truly doesn't have
anything to do with you...
It's him... My love...
My darling Gray.
[JUVIA] I can just picture
us... Sitting in a patio café
by the river... The warm
sun shining down on us
while we drink tea and talk
into the evening hours...
Or maybe we'd talk forever.
[happy sigh]
Hey! Make with
the tea already!
And put some iron in it!
If you want
tea so badly,
then just go
inside and get some!
I'm staying right here
where I am, in the sunlight,
cuz I don't
wanna get rusty!
So they're just gonna
have to bring it to me!
[JUVIA] I'm warning you...
Hmmm?
[JUVIA] Don't you
dare get in my way.
What's the big deal?
We're just three friends hangin'
out, havin' some tea together.
That's true, but I think
three's a crowd...
So just get lost!
I just said I don't
wanna get rusty!
So do you
understand now?
Who, me? No, of
course I don't...
You sound crazy.
[JUVIA] No one
understands me.
[BIXLOW] How ya doin', Wendy?
[WENDY] I'm hanging in there!
[BIXLOW] We're getting
pretty close...
It's just over
this mountain pass.
[WENDY] That's great!
[rolling thunder]
Well that's weird.
A thunderstorm?
I've always heard
mountain weather
is unpredictable.
[BIXLOW] What in the--?!
That storm just
came outta nowhere!
[ERIGOR] What was the weather
was like yesterday...?
I can't remember.
[BIXLOW] It's that guy who
calls himself Grim Reaper...
He's like one big,
walking black cloud.
[WENDY] He used
to be called Erigor.
He was with the
dark guild Eisenwald.
Those names mean
nothing to me now.
I don't know Erigor...
or Eisenwald...
[BIXLOW] C'mon,
gimme a break, man.
You have gotta have
the world's worst memory.
Maybe...
But I do know
what's coming next.
Cloudbursts from above!
[ERIGOR] And tornadoes
ripping through the air!
I can create weather patterns
that defy the very laws
of nature and destroy pesky
little flies like you!
What'd you say?
Don't worry, Bixlow...
I can support you.
[BIXLOW] Listen up, ya
windbag! We ain't no flies!
We're the Fairy
Tail wizards
who are gonna
kick your butt!
Powerful gusts...
from below!
[WENDY screams]
[ERIGOR] What's the matter?
Are you nothing but talk?
[BIXLOW] Dammit!
[WENDY] I can
heal you...
There's not
enough time!
[magic power charging up]
[BIXLOW] Uh-oh.
Fairy Tail...
I don't know it... However...
I do know that
dark skies are coming.
A violent thunderstorm!
Raining down from above!
Stand back!
I can stop it!
Sky Dragon... Roar!
I don't understand
this guy...
It's like he's
soulless.
Followed by lightning
directly behind you.
Too slow, pal!
Huh?
[BIXLOW] I've already
moved their souls
into different dolls!
So now you're gonna get it!
Point-blank Baryon Formation!
No, he got away!
What the heck?! I didn't
know that he could fly!
[ERIGOR] Neither did I...
Seems I had forgotten.
Can you tell me who
you people are again?
Seriously?
Did he actually forget that
he was fighting against us?
Sky Dragon... Wing Attack!
[ERIGOR] Are you really
foolish enough to use wind magic
against a man who can
control the weather?
That's your last mistake!
Wendy, you gotta
get out of the way!
[COWS moo]
[ERIGOR] I can create
a wind so powerful,
nothing can withstand it!
[BIXLOW screams]
[BIXLOW] It's
raining stinky cows!
I'm so sorry... It's
my fault that you got hurt!
Are you in there Bixlow?!
[COWS moo]
[PANTHERLILY] The Infinity
Clock has been assembled
and taken by the Oración Seis.
Yes, they have it...
So what are your people
going to do about it now?
Do you have a plan?
I've made several
calculations...
But I'm afraid the
situation has suddenly
grown exponentially
more complex. Alas...
Even I can't seem
to comprehend it.
Now I get it!
You were following us so
you could ask us for help!
We're fellow
Exceeds after all.
[SAMUEL] Yes, your
assumption is correct...
If things get any more out
of hand, I fear the situation
could become too much for
humans to sufficiently handle.
Oh, so that's
what you think now?
Funny, I thought you said
Zentopia's teachings were
all that mattered to you.
While I truly treasure
our doctrine,
adaptability is paramount
to one's survival.
Makes sense
to me.
Okay, then go on
and tell us what
we can do to help you.
It's not that simple...
The truth is, all you ever
seem to think about is fish,
and brother Lily is nothing more
than pure, mindless, brawn.
What'd you say?!
You're cruisin' for
a bruisin', Sammy!
Tell me, Carla...
You possess the power
of clairvoyance...
Have you sensed anything
out of the ordinary?
I've had several visions,
although none have
been very clear...
They're dark and ominous.
Any that were
related to the book?
Think carefully.
A few... In fact,
they struck me
as some sort of warning.
The clock was never
meant to be assembled...
Apparently, the pieces were
originally guarded by Zentopia.
And now here we are...
facing an incomprehensible task
that we must
complete without fail.
So you wanna
know the future?
Is that it?
What is most
unsettling to me...
Is the possibility that
the teachings of Zentopia
are being twisted, and
used to commit atrocities.
It looks like we were
too late on this one.
We have failed
in our mission.
I don't get it...
This is wrong...
Why're we being forced
to attack churches?
[metallic clanging]
[MARY] It totally
doesn't make any sense...
[GUTMAN grunts]
[GUTMAN] We were given this
mission by his eminence!
We're not supposed
to question him!
Dontcha know that's bad?!
He's telepathic?
Those two are
not Oración Seis...
They're with the
Legion Platoon!
[MARY cries out]
[GUTMAN] I spy some
filthy guild wizards.
[GAJEEL] You work
for Zentopia, dontcha?!
Is this in-fighting?
It's awful... Those
priests... How could you?!
[GUTMAN] His eminence speaks
the word of the archbishop.
His words are sacred!
They are holy law!
So if he says we gotta bust up
a church, we go bust it up!
Don't forget that
we are rewarded whenever
we follow his words...
and we're punished
whenever we don't!
[GAJEEL] He's insane.
[MARY yells]
[GUTMAN] You dirty sinner!
I'll make you go boom!
No... Stop!
[MARY screams]
[GAJEEL] Whoa!
What was that?!
Some kinda explosion?
No... It was somethin' else.
Careful Gajeel,
he's dangerous!
Speaking of
punishment, pal...
It's time for yours!
[GUTMAN] I can tell you two have
a lot of magic power inside!
You're gonna be
so much fun to play with!
[GAJEEL screams]
[JUVIA screams]
[GUTMAN] What pretty lights!
Your ruptures are so cool!
What's the matter
with this guy?!
Such strange magic...
I've never seen it before.
It's Rupture magic...
It's, like, mega powerful.
He can take his target's
internal magic power
and expand it until it ruptures.
We don't stand a chance.
[GUTMAN] Now everybody's
gonna go boom-boom!
Juvia! We gotta
keep fighting!
There's no way
I'm gonna give up!
[GUTMAN] Isn't this fun?!
I'm glad you still have
so much power left 'cause
I can keep playin' with you...
'til it's all gone.
[GUTMAN] Oh sorry,
did that hurt...?
Well, there's a whole lot
more where that came from.
I just don't
understand... Why would
the archbishop set this monster
free to attack churches?
It's, like, so wrong...
It goes against
Zentopia's teachings.
[GILDARTS] Hello?!
Is anybody in there?
[NUN A] Outsiders
are strictly forbidden
from coming inside.
C'mon, you don't
have to be like that...
Dontcha wanna be friends?
Hey!
That was way too direct.
Flirting is a lot
like throwing a pitch,
you wanna go fast and direct.
Well, It looks like
you struck out to me.
Alright... I guess
we got no other choice.
Laki... I need you now.
Listen to me...
No, you listen to me,
try anything funny
and Cana's getting
an earful!
Some of it will be true,
but for most of it,
I'm just gonna
make stuff up.
Calm down... I think
that you've got
the wrong idea.
[GILDARTS] Take a good
look at the monastery...
[GILDARTS] I gotta say, your
magic sure comes in handy.
[LAKI] Hey!
Don't try to cop a feel while
we're sneaking around like this!
[punch]
[GILDARTS] Ow...!
Aw man, that hurt!
[fart]
[gasps]
Sorry that just
slipped out.
[MONKS AND NUNS]
Outsiders... Outsiders...
Outsiders...
[LAKI] They've spotted us...
And we were doing so
good there for a while.
This is totally all
your fault, you know.
Outsiders... Outsiders...
Something's strange.
The little hairs on
the back of my neck
are doing hand-stands!
There's an easier
way to say these guys
creep you out.
[LAKI] Wood Make:
The Heart Feels Distant!
[GILDARTS] All of you
better back off! Right now!
Oh no! Beating up
monks and nuns
has gotta be
rotten karma!
[MONKS AND NUNS]
Outsiders... Outsiders...
[LAKI] This is so bizarre...
What's wrong with them?!
[GILDARTS] I dunno but they're
gettin' on my last nerve.
[LAKI] Get away from us!
Outsiders... Outsiders...
You guys just invaded
my personal space!
How could you just
kill them like that?!
I didn't kill 'em,
look closer...
They're not even
living creatures.
They're like bricks...
Pieces of earth and wood
to build some kind of puppets.
I've never heard of
a magic that can do that.
I don't trust this Zentopia...
Gotta wonder
what they're hiding.
That bunch. They've got secrets.
Some very dark secrets.
I think we've stumbled
onto something
far more sinister than
even the master suspected.
Sure did... But ol' Macao
was right on the money
sending us to
bust up this party.
[MONKS AND NUNS]
Outsiders... Outsiders...
We got a lot to do!
So let's get to work!
♪
[HAPPY] Is it just me, or
does the Oración Seis seem
a heck of a lot stronger
than they were last time?
[NATSU] Who knows?
Maybe it's just because
they think they're gonna win.
[HAPPY] Yeah, but
that's what we think, too!
We can't both be right!
Somebody's gotta lose!
[NATSU] Right! So let's
go kick their butts
and put a stop to their
quest for world abomination!
[HAPPY] Thank goodness it's
not a vocabulary contest.
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next time: Anti-Link!
[NATSU] Well it's not, so
we're definitely winning!
[HAPPY] See? That's exactly
what I'm talking about!
Both sides think
they're gonna win!
[NATSU] What's wrong with that?
Somebody's gotta be right!