- Makarov:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL--"
- Mirajane:
MY LITTLE SISTER LISANNA
AND NATSU HAVE BEEN CLOSE
EVER SINCE THEY WERE YOUNG.
ONE TRAGIC DAY THERE
WAS AN ACCIDENT
AND WE ALL THOUGHT
SHE WAS DEAD.
IT WAS TOUGH, BUT WE
MANAGED TO COPE
WITH THE PAIN
AND GET ON WITH OUR LIVES.
- Natsu:
WHEN WE WENT TO EDOLAS, WE MET
WHAT WE THOUGHT WAS
HER WEIRD TWIN.
BUT IT TURNED OUT
TO ACTUALLY BE HER!
THE REAL LISANNA!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: FAIRY TAIL'S S-CLASS
WIZARD PROMOTION TRIAL
WAS WELL UNDERWAY
WHEN THE FEARSOME GRIMOIRE HEART
APPEARED AND LAUNCHED AN ATTACK.
OUR FRIENDS STRUGGLED
AGAINST THE LOST MAGIC USERS
KNOWN AS THE SEVEN KIN.
EVEN MAKAROV FELL IN BATTLE
TO THEIR FIENDISH LEADER.
- I'LL TAKE DOWN MASTER HADES!
AND I'LL DO IT
WITH MY OWN TWO HANDS!
- I PITY YOU, YOUNG MAN.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
THE POWER OF FAMILY!
- Narrator: NATSU WAS ABLE
TO DIG DEEP INSIDE
AND DEFEAT THE GOD SLAYER
ZANCROW.
HOWEVER...
- Happy: ...
- ( laughing )
- NO WAY.
THAT WEAK LITTLE DRAGON HUNTER
ACTUALLY BEAT ME?
- Makarov: HE EMPTIED OUT
ALL OF HIS OWN MAGIC POWER
IN ORDER TO CREATE A VESSEL FOR
CAPTURING HIS OPPONENT'S FLAMES.
THAT STRATEGY SEEMS IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT, HE DOESN'T KNOW
THE MEANING OF THAT WORD.
THOUGH I STILL NEED TO SCOLD HIM
FOR BEING SO RECKLESS.
- Natsu:
GRAMPS.
LET'S KEEP FIGHTING.
I LEARNED A VALUABLE LESSON
FROM GILDARTS.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO KNOW
YOUR LIMITS, AND FALL BACK.
BUT NOW, NOW IS NOT
ONE OF THOSE TIMES.
THESE PEOPLE MADE AN ENEMY
OUT OF FAIRY TAIL.
WE'VE GOT TO SHOW THEM
NOBODY CAN DO THAT.
YOU CAN NEVER DEFEAT A GUILD
THAT HAS AS MUCH HEART AS WE DO.
NOT WITHOUT A FIGHT.
RIGHT, GRAMPS?
- NATSU!
- IF YOU'RE INDEED
ALL ONE BIG FAMILY,
I SUPPOSE IT'S FITTING
THAT YOU SHOULD FALL TOGETHER.
- MIRA, YOU'VE GOT TO USE
SATAN'S SOUL.
- Azuma:
SOUNDS INTRIGUING.
- I CAN'T, I'M STILL RECOVERING
FROM THE LAST TIME I USED IT.
- I KNOW YOU, YOU'RE SISTERS.
FROM FAIRY TAIL'S
LEGENDARY STRAUSS FAMILY.
AND IF THAT'S TRULY THE CASE,
THEN YOU--
YOU MUST BE THE ONE
KNOWN AS THE SHE-DEVIL.
- Mirajane:
THAT'S WHO I USED TO BE.
- Lisanna:
BUT SHE'S STILL JUST AS STRONG
AS SHE EVER WAS BACK THEN.
- IS THAT SO?
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO BATTLE
WITH A WARRIOR
WHO POSSESSES THE POWER
OF A TRUE DEMON.
ARE YOU NOW TOO WEAK
TO FULFILL MY WISH?
- WELL, I'M READY
TO TAKE YOU ON.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, LISANNA?
YOU NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE.
HE'S TOO STRONG.
YOU CAN'T BEAT HIM.
- I WOULD PREFER
NOT TO DO THIS,
BUT YOU HAVE FORCED MY HAND.
- NO!
- LISANNA!
- IN THREE MINUTES,
THE ROOTS HOLDING HER
WILL DETONATE.
THAT WON'T WORK.
TRYING TO PULL IT APART
IS A WASTE OF TIME AND ENERGY.
YOUR ONLY HOPE OF STOPPING IT
IS BY DEFEATING ME.
- I CAN'T...MOVE!
- YOU COWARD!
- YOU SAY THAT, AND YET I AM THE
ONE WHO IS NOT AFRAID TO FIGHT.
- BE CAREFUL.
- I DON'T HAVE
MUCH MAGIC POWER LEFT.
BUT THE ONLY WAY TO SAVE HER
IS TO FIGHT!
- AT LAST, A WORTHY FOE.
IT FEELS AMAZING!
- NO, MIRA!
KEEP YOUR MIND ON THE BATTLE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
CHAIN BURST, NOW.
HER STRENGTH...
- LET MY SISTER GO!
- Azuma:
HER INTENSITY...
Azuma:
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE FELT SO ALIVE.
Azuma: YOU SHOULD KNOW
BETTER THAN TO LOOK AWAY.
NOW, BURST CLAW.
- MIRA!
NO-OO!
- EVIL EXPLOSION!
- VERY IMPRESSIVE.
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
LET'S KEEP GOING.
- IT'S POINTLESS,
HE'S WAY TOO STRONG FOR ME.
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MAGIC POWER
TO KEEP THIS UP.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- ARE YOU RUNNING AWAY FROM ME?
STAND AND FIGHT.
IT'S THE ONLY HOPE YOU HAVE
OF SAVING YOUR SISTER.
NOW, COME HERE AND FACE ME.
DO IT WHILE THERE'S
STILL TIME.
- I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T WANT IT
TO END THIS WAY.
BUT I JUST DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH POWER LEFT TO BEAT HIM.
THE WAY I AM RIGHT NOW,
I'M JUST TOO WEAK.
- YOU'RE GIVING UP?
- LISTEN, I'M NOT
GIVING UP HOPE.
I HAVE FAITH SOMEBODY IN
OUR GUILD WILL HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO TAKE THIS GUY DOWN.
I KNOW THEY WILL.
- BUT, WHY?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND, WHY NOW?
- SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO KNOW
WHEN YOU'VE BEEN BEATEN.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY, LISANNA.
I PROMISE YOU,
I WON'T LET YOU DIE AGAIN.
- ( alarm sounds )
- HEY, ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
MIRA?
BIG SIS,
WAKE UP.
PLEASE, WAKE UP.
MIRA, NO!
NO-OO!
- THIS PATH I'VE TRAVELED,
SUCH AN EXHAUSTING JOURNEY.
LONG, AND FULL OF TURMOIL.
BUT TODAY, IT APPEARS
I'VE FINALLY REACHED IT'S END.
AND ONCE I'VE FOUND LORD ZEREF,
MY SOUL CAN BE AT PEACE.
WHO ARE YOU?
- YOU'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR ME?
I SEE.  YOU MUST BE
ONE OF THOSE
SOWING THE SEEDS
OF CONFLICT AND DEATH.
IT'S TRAGIC,
FOR YOU HAVE MADE ME
QUITE ANGRY.
- Pantherlily:
WENDY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- Wendy:
YEAH, I'M FINE.
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY I CAN'T HEAL THEM.
HOW COME IT ISN'T WORKING?
- MASTER'S WOUNDS MAY BE
TOO SEVERE
TO BE HEALED BY SKY MAGIC.
I'M AFRAID THERE MAY BE NOTHING
WE CAN DO FOR HIM
AT THE MOMENT.
- AND NATSU?
- I'M NOT ENTIRELY SURE
WHY HE'S NOT RESPONDING.
BUT IT FEELS AS IF THERE'S
SOMETHING GETTING IN THE WAY.
- OH, NO.
POOR GUYS.
- Makarov: WENDY...
- MASTER!
- I HAD FAITH THAT YOU WOULD
FIND US.
WHAT A BLESSING.
ARE YOU WELL, MY CHILD?
- YES, SIR.
- I'M AN OLD MAN, BUT NATSU--
HE IS OUR GUILD'S FUTURE.
SAVE HIM.
- BUT MASTER, YOU'RE HURT.
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE YOU HERE
IN PAIN LIKE THAT.
IF YOU HANG ON, I'M SURE I CAN
FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO HELP BOTH OF YOU.
- HIS SCARF, IT'S BEEN TAINTED.
PLEASE, YOU MUST TRY
TO RETURN IT TO NORMAL.
- I NEED TO FIX HIS SCARF?
- THE MALEVOLENT FORCE
THAT HAS TAINTED IT
IS WHAT'S PREVENTING HIM
FROM BEING HEALED.
- OKAY, I'LL TRY.
- DOES ANYBODY KNOW
WHAT COULD HAVE MADE HIS SCARF
TURN BLACK IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- THIS CREEPY GUY
WHO WOULDN'T STOP CRYING
THAT WE RAN INTO EARLIER
WAS THE ONE THAT DID IT.
- GRIMOIRE HEART
IS HERE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE.
DO YOU THINK THIS CRYING MAN
YOU MET-- COULD HE BE ZEREF?
- IT'S HIM.
AFTER YEARS OF SEARCHING,
LORD ZEREF IS STANDING
RIGHT BEFORE MY VERY EYES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
- YOU PEOPLE HAVE COME HERE
BECAUSE YOU DESPERATELY SEEK
MY POWER.
- IT IS YOUR ENTIRE EXISTENCE
WE SEEK, LORD ZEREF.
- I WON'T INVOLVE MYSELF
IN MANKIND'S AFFAIRS.
NOT FOR THE REMAINDER
OF THIS CURRENT ERA.
I HAVE NO DESIRE TO SEE PEOPLE
WAGE WAR AND DIE.
I ORDER YOU TO STOP
YOUR ATTACK ON THIS ISLAND
AND LEAVE AT ONCE!
- THIS CAN'T BE RIGHT.
WAR AND DEATH
DO NOT INTEREST HIM?
HE SEEMS CONSCIOUS,
BUT PERHAPS,
HE'S NOT YET AWARE.
IS THIS TRULY HIM?
IS THIS WHAT THEY CALL
HIS STATE OF REST?
- YOUR PRESENCE HAS
MADE ME ANGRY.
- WHAT THE--
WATCH IT, YOU BIG BRUTE!
- YOU'RE ONE TO TALK!
- MY GUARDIAN SAINT BEAST,
DEAR BELCUSAS, THE THUNDERCLAP.
- DID HE SAY,
"BELCUSAS THE THUNDERCLAP?"
- THAT'S A PRETTY
MANLY NICKNAME.
- ANGELS QUICKLY FLY FROM FATE,
ALAS, A DEVIL ALWAYS
LIES IN WAIT.
- I'M SICK OF YOUR ANGEL
AND DEVIL CRAP.
SO QUIT TALKING GARBAGE
AND COME FIGHT ME
LIKE A REAL MAN!
- BELCUSAS, GO GIVE THAT MAN
THE FIGHT HE SO DESIRES.
- I WAS TALKING TO YOU,
PRETTY BOY!
- FAIRY MACHINE GUN LEPRECHAUN!
NOT EVEN A SCRATCH?
- SO YOU LIKE MONSTERS, HUH?
TAKE OVER, BEAST SOUL!
HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
WOULD YOU HURRY UP AND JUST TURN
HIM TO STONE ALREADY?
- THAT ONLY WORKS
ON HUMANS, MEATHEAD!
- NOT HIM, YOU IDIOT.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT THE MAN.
DO YOUR WEIRD STATUE SPELL
ON HIM.
- IT WON'T WORK ON HIM
BECAUSE HE'S WEARING GLASSES.
- WHAT?
THAT'S THE LAMEST EXCUSE
I'VE EVER HEARD.
- I SHOULD USE IT ON YOU--
- SPARKS OF PASSION ERUPT
INTO FLAMES
BETWEEN THOSE IN LOVE.
- Both:
WE ARE NOT IN LOVE, OKAY?
- Evergreen: KEEP
THAT ONE BUSY FOR NOW.
- HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'VE FIGURED OUT
HOW HIS MAGIC WORKS.
HE USE SUMMONING SPELLS
JUST LIKE LUCY.
AND ALL SUMMONING WIZARDS
HAVE ONE GLARING FLAW--
THEIR BODIES ARE WEAK!
- ( sneezes )
GOT YOU NOW...
- I AM LORD OF THE UNDERWORLD.
AND MY ARM IS A JET-BLACK SWORD
THAT CLEAVES THROUGH ALL.
AND YOU...
WILL FADE BEYOND THE DARKNESS!
- OH, NO.  EVERGREEN!
THIS GUY'S MAGIC--
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
- I SUPPOSE THAT I COULD EXPLAIN
HOW IT WORKS,
BUT IT WOULD PROVE
FAR TOO DIFFICULT TO UNDERSTAND
FOR SCUM LIKE YOU.
- SAY WHAT?
- IT SPRINGS FROM A PLACE
VERY CLOSE TO THE DARKEST DEPTHS
OF MAGIC.
AND AS A RESULT, THE SIDE
EFFECTS IT BURDENS ME WITH
ARE EXTREMELY HEAVY
AND POWERFUL.
OH, I WALK THE PATH OF LIFE
LADEN WITH THE WEIGHT
OF TRAGEDY.
- UH...
- BUT NOW, WE'VE LEARNED
THE GREAT WIZARD ZEREF
IS ALMOST WITHIN OUR REACH.
HE WILL LIFT THIS TRAGIC BURDEN
FROM OUR SHOULDERS AND USHER IN
A NEW AND WONDROUS AGE.
- WAIT, THAT'S THE GUY
FROM EARLIER.
- ZEREF?
THE LEGENDARY BLACK WIZARD?
THAT WAS HIM?
BUT, HE SHOULDN'T BE ALIVE.
MUCH LESS ON THIS ISLAND.
- WE'LL ENTER
THE GRAND MAGIC WORLD.
- THE GRAND MAGIC WORLD?
BUT WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
- A TRUE AND PRIMAL REALM
RULED BY FEAR AND DARKNESS,
AS IT SHOULD RIGHTLY BE.
- RULED BY DARKNESS?
- A WIZARD'S PROVINCE,
WHERE THOSE WHO DO NOT SHARE
OUR ABILITIES PERISH
OR TREMBLE AS THEY PRAY
FOR DEATH.
ISN'T IT MARVELOUS?
A WORLD MADE
ENTIRELY FOR OUR KIND ALONE.
COMPLETELY FREE FROM THOSE
IGNORANT OR FRIGHTENED
OF THE BLACK ARTS.
- WHEN AT LAST ZEREF TAKES
HIS DESTINED PLACE AS RULER,
- THE GRAND MAGIC WORLD
WILL BE UPON US.
- THOSE WITHOUT MAGIC POWER
WILL BE ANNIHILATED.
AND WE SHALL INHERIT
THIS MAGICAL UTOPIA.
I'VE WAITED SO LONG
FOR THIS GLORIOUS DAY.
AND AT LAST,
IT'S DAWN IS SOON TO BREAK.
- NO WAY.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WHAT HE'S SAYING,
IT'S PURE MADNESS!
- WHAT IS THAT?
IF I TOUCH IT, IT WILL BORE
THROUGH ME, AS WELL.
OBTAINING LORD ZEREF
IS AT STAKE.
I HAVE TO TAKE THE RISK.
LOST MAGIC
FORWARD ARC OF TIME!
SPEEDING FORTH THE FLOW OF TIME,
I WILL TRAP YOU IN ITS COURSE!
I'VE GOT YOU.
- IT COMES.
THE PREDATORY DEATH.
- ARC OF TIME!
- PLEASE TELL ME
WHO YOU ARE.
- ( screaming )
LUMINOUS MINUTES!
ALTHOUGH YOUR FULL POWER
MAY BE THE STUFF OF LEGENDS,
NOW, THIS PITIFUL STATE YOU'RE
IN IS SIMPLY NO MATCH FOR ME.
DON'T YOU DARE TO UNDERESTIMATE
THE LEADER OF THE SEVEN KIN!
BUT LORD ZEREF, DO NOT WORRY.
FOR NOW WE POSSESS
ALL THE KEYS NECESSARY
TO AWAKEN YOU.
- PLEASE STOP.
- AT LONG LAST,
I HAVE HIM!  LORD ZEREF
IS IN MY HANDS!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy:
WE ALL GOT SPLIT UP.
I REALLY HOPE EVERYONE
ELSE IS OKAY.
- Natsu:
I'M SURE ERZA AND GRAY ARE COOL.
AND LUCY ALWAYS SEEMS
TO GET BY SOMEHOW.
- Happy: ACTUALLY, ELFMAN IS THE
ONE I'M REALLY WORRIED ABOUT.
- Natsu:
I'D NEVER SAY IT TO HIS FACE
BUT HE KIND OF CRACKS
UNDER PRESSURE, HUH?
- Happy: YEAH, AND THE FACT THAT
HE'S OUT THERE WITH EVERGREEN
WORRIES ME TOO.  I MEAN,
THOSE THUNDER LEGION GUYS
CAN BE PRETTY WEIRD.
- Happy and Natsu: ...
- Natsu: MAYBE THEIR WEIRDNESS
WILL CANCEL EACH OTHER'S OUT
AND THEY WILL BE
AWESOME TOGETHER.
- Happy:
THEY'RE IN LOVE!
- Natsu: OH MAN, HAVEN'T
HEARD THAT ONE IN A WHILE!