Hey, Dad.
[NATSU]
Where are you?
Come back! I need you!
[LUCY]
On July 7th, in the year 777,
Natsu's foster father,
the Fire Dragon King Igneel,
mysteriously disappeared,
and Natsu was left all alone.
The young Dragon Slayer
searched everywhere.
Even after he joined
the Fairy Tail guild,
Natsu never gave up
hope that one day,
he would reunite with the only
father he had ever known.
But when that time came,
it wasn't the reunion
he had expected.
[ZIRCONIS] They granted humans
what would come to be known
as Dragon Slaying magic.
And with this new power in hand,
mankind joined the war.
The Dragon Slayers'
immeasurable power
quickly turned the
tide of the war.
We were so overwhelmed
that victory seemed certain
for the dragons
on the other side.
But no one predicted
the travesty
that would come to pass.
The Dragon Slayers
became so powerful,
they eventually turned
on the very dragons
that had given them
their strength.
It was a massacre.
There was one man whose
power was so terrible,
he bathed the countryside
in the blood of my kin.
The very mention of his
name still scares me.
This man slayed
countless dragons
and soaked in their blood.
He used his power so often
that his skin turned to scales,
his teeth sharpened into fangs,
and he stopped being
human altogether.
That is the fate
that awaits all who practice
Dragon Slayer magic.
All the bones you see here
belong to the victims
of that monster.
Despite his human origins,
he became the king
of all dragonkind.
And the war that he gave rise to
came to be known as
the Dragon King Festival.
His name, was Acnologia.
Once a human being,
now a dragon, cloaked
in wings of darkness.
Was he attracted by the
concentration of power?
Or does he know?
Perhaps he comes to find Zeref.
That sound! There's
no mistaking it!
It's Acnologia!
[roars]
[NATSU screaming]
[IGNEEL] I'm sorry, son,
but I never did leave you.
[IGNEEL]
In fact,
I've been closer than
you ever could've guessed.
[growling]
That's him. The King
of the Dragons.
[roars]
[IGNEEL roaring]
I can't believe it.
Igneel was inside him?
How? Is that possible?
Maybe. Do you have one, Gajeel?
Don't really know,
but the pain's gone.
Mine's calming down.
How's yours?
I'm fine. Let's get moving.
Where's that guy with
the book? He was right here.
[STING]
He can't be too far.
Wendy. Gracious,
are you all right?
Yeah.
You had us really worried there.
Sorry
Carla, what's happening?
[roaring]
[CANA] Where did they come
from? Whose side are they on?
[VIJEETER] I know the
black one is Acnologia.
But what about the red dragon?
What am I a dragon expert now?
Guys, I'm not sure, but if
I didn't know any better,
I'd think that other dragon
was fighting Acnologia.
Well, Acnologia's
obviously our enemy.
But maybe he's on our side.
And if he wins,
will he turn on us?
We sure could use his help.
Why are they here?
I can't answer that.
Wait a minute.
Do you guys think he's back
to finish what he started?
I highly doubt that's the case.
But if they keep this up,
there won't be any
trace of Magnolia left.
So, why'd they come back now?
And why are there two of them?
We're doomed.
Humans don't stand a chance
when faced with the
strength of a dragon.
Who's the dragon
fighting Acnologia?
Where'd he come from?
Flames?
So he's a fire dragon.
Wait, is he?
They must be stopped.
I won't let them get
in the way of our plans.
Tell me what to do,
Lord Mard Geer.
[MARD GEER]
Dark Winged Acnologia.
Fire Dragon King Igneel.
Your existence is nothing more
than an obstacle I shan't
tolerate any longer.
So I've made a slight
change of strategy.
Now you will be destroyed.
[BOTH roaring]
[MARD GEER]
O ye who is forgotten.
We're gonna be okay, aren't we?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
What's goin' on, Salamander?
I mean is that really Igneel?
What was up with all that
stuff about being inside you?
[NATSU]
I have no idea.
He left.
I looked for him for so long.
I'm sorry.
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU]
Dad! We gotta talk. Now!
[ERZA]
What's he doing?
Oh yeah!
[yelling]
Natsu, I told you,
we'll talk later.
Tell me now! Why did you
disappear and leave me?
Oh, and if you were
with me the whole time,
why didn't you say something?
Do Wendy and Gajeel have
dragons inside them, too?
And what happened that day?
On July 7th, the
day you left me!
Come on. You owe me!
[IGNEEL]
Enough!
[NATSU yelping]
That was close!
Quit distracting him!
[ACNOLOGIA roars]
[roaring]
[LEVY]
It burns!
[GAJEEL]
Stay behind me!
I'm... boiling.
That's a manly dragon.
That heat's intense.
This is bad! Like really bad!
It feels like I'm in an oven.
And we're standing
way over here.
So freakin' hot!
[LUMMYS screaming]
That's unbelievable.
It's almost like the sun is
crashing down from the sky.
It's over. Don't you think?
I dunno. He definitely
sounds like he's in pain.
And if that dragon can't
take the heat, nobody can.
Yeah. We better find
someplace to hide.
I don't think
that's gonna help us.
[roaring]
Amazing.
It's the Fire Dragon Roar.
Oh wow. That fireball's huge.
You're right about that.
Their battle, it
could destroy Magnolia.
It's hard to believe.
So, you killed him?
Not at all. Just wait and see.
[ACNOLOGIA roaring]
[NATSU]
Uh!
Wait! That fireball did nothing?
Seriously?
How could he've
survived those flames?
He doesn't even have a scratch.
That attack should've
destroyed him.
I'm not sure he can die.
Is he immortal?
So, how do we get rid of
somebody who's immortal?
Great question, but
I'm not really sure.
Hope for the best. That's
all we can do right now.
I'm fired up now.
[IGNEEL]
Son...
[NATSU]
Huh?
You're a pest.
What do you mean by that?!
You sure have a weird way of
showin' that you missed me!
[IGNEEL]
I've already told you,
we'll talk about
everything later.
I've got a job I need you to do.
[NATSU]
What kinda job?
You are in one of those
guilds, aren't you?
Well, I'd like to
officially hire you.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[IGNEEL]
Over there.
[IGNEEL] Make sure you get
a good look at that guy.
See that book?
That's the Book of E.N.D.
So, what do I do?
I want you to steal that book.
Why do I have to be
the one to do it?
[IGNEEL] Because you're
the only one who can, Natsu.
Plus, he's the one
responsible for all of this.
I assumed you wouldn't
need a better reason
than that to want to fight him.
He did this?
[IGNEEL]
Now listen,
you are not to open
or destroy that book
under any circumstances.
Just take it, you understand?
How much does it pay?
What?
I work for a guild now!
I don't do these kinda
things for free!
[IGNEEL growls]
Very well.
For payment, I will tell you
everything you wish to know.
[chuckles] Sounds
like a deal to me!
[IGNEEL]
Heh. Now get that book.
[NATSU]
You better keep your promise!
Don't even think
about going anywhere.
[IGNEEL]
I won't.
You know, I'm gonna
hold you to that.
Now I'm all fired up!
Make sure you get a
good look at that guy.
See that book?
That's the Book of E.N.D.
So, what do I do?
I want you to steal that book.
Why do I have to be
the one to do it?
Now listen, you are not to
open or destroy that book
under any circumstances.
Just take it, you understand?
[chuckles] Sounds
like a deal to me.
[IGNEEL]
Heh. Now, get that book.
[NATSU]
Now I'm all fired up!
[NATSU yelling]
Who might you be?
[NATSU]
Me? I'm Igneel's son!
[MARD GEER]
The son of a dragon, eh?
[NATSU]
I'm taking that book!
And stopping the Faces!
Oh?
It's over. You're about
to get thrashed.
[MARD GEER]
Curse of Thorns!
How could he dodge a curse
that he's never seen before?
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon...
...Iron Fist!
[yelling]
[MARD GEER]
Kyoka, can you hear me?
[gasps]
[KYOKA]
Lord Mard Geer?
[MARD GEER] These dragons are
more trouble than I thought.
So, I've decided to
detonate the Faces sooner.
[MARD GEER] You're in the
control room, aren't you?
[KYOKA]
Yes.
But you should know, my Lord,
Keyes and Seilah
have been defeated,
which leaves us with no way
of controlling the Chairman.
[MARD GEER]
No need to worry.
Once the Faces
have been activated,
anyone can trigger
the detonation.
Even you.
[gasps]
[MARD GEER]
The main Lacrima should be
in the center of
the control room.
Now all you must
do is use Body Link
to connect yourself with it.
[KYOKA]
Body Link?
[MARD GEER]
By doing so,
you will make yourself
the detonator key,
which will allow us
to expedite our plan.
[MARD GEER]
If we can detonate the Faces,
we can nullify these
wizards for good.
And if we're lucky,
we may be able
to drain the dragons'
life force.
Then, our Master E.N.D.
will finally be revived.
[MARD GEER]
Victory will be ours.
Now, Kyoka, do it.
[KYOKA] With all due
respect, Lord Mard Geer,
if I were to link
my own curse power
with the power
of the Faces...
...then I would die.
[MARD GEER]
So what? Are you afraid to die?
[gasps]
[KYOKA]
Not at all.
If it means Tartaros
completes its mission,
I will gladly give my life.
[BOTH]
Everything we do...
[MARD GEER, KYOKA]
We do for our Lord Zeref!
[KYOKA groaning]
[screaming]
What are those things?
I think they're some
kind of markers.
Um, guys, I have a really
bad feeling about this.
Yeah, I'm right there with ya.
[KYOKA] These are all the
locations of the Faces
throughout the continent.
And now the Body
Link is complete,
which means,
you're now looking at
the official new detonator.
You're what?
Did she say she's
using Body Link?
So that means,
she's a part of it?
Why would she do that?
They must've wanted the
Faces' detonation accelerated.
[chuckles]
I've just made things
very easy for you.
If you kill me, then
you will stop the Faces.
[KYOKA]
Though it really doesn't matter,
because I'll die either way.
[ERZA] Well, you certainly
are sure of yourself.
But have you ever even
considered the possibility
that you could lose?
[KYOKA]
No need.
For I have something you don't.
I am Kyoka, Goddess
of the Slave Planet!
[gasps]
And now I embrace my
true Etherious Form.
What?
[LUCY]
While Igneel and Acnologia
continue their intense battle,
Kyoka uses body link magic to
become the Faces' detonator.
Now it's up to one of Fairy
Tail's strongest warriors
to defeat her and stop
the accelerating countdown.
But even Erza is beginning
to feel helpless at the sight
of the Goddess of the slave
planet in her Etherious Form.
Next Time:
"Tartaros Chapter 00:00."
Even when all seems lost,
there's still something left.