- Natsu: PREVIOUSLY
ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
- Happy: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
JELLAL'S ALIVE!
THIS IS BAD, GUYS.
- Lucy:
ERZA'S IN SERIOUS TROUBLE
IF WE DON'T GET
WENDY HERE FAST.
- Racer: I'LL SHOW YOU
FAST, BLONDIE.
- Gray:
QUIT STANDING AROUND, NATSU.
I'LL HOLD OFF THE SPEED FREAK.
GET TO ERZA! QUICKLY!
- Racer:
I'LL SHOW YOU "QUICKLY!"
- Natsu: OH! ENOUGH
WITH THE FAST TALK!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
THE WORTH WOODSEA...
ITS TRANQUILITY DISRUPTED
BY A LONE MAN
HEADING DEEP
INTO ITS HEART.
- ( Happy groans )
- YOU OKAY, LITTLE BUDDY?
- NATSU, WHERE ARE WE?
- NO TALKING.  YOU GOT TO
TRY TO REST UP, ALL RIGHT?
- BUT JELLAL IS OUT
THERE SOMEWHERE.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T
STICK AROUND LONG.
- Male voice:
NATSU!
- ( gasps )
WHAT THE HECK?
- Happy: WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY'D YOU STOP?
- Male voice:
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- THIS TREE
IS TALKING TO ME.
- ( Happy speaking )
- Hibiki:
CAN YOU HEAR ME, NATSU?
- YES, GREAT TREE.
- GREAT WHAT?
THIS IS HIBIKI FROM
BLUE PEGASUS.
ANYWAY, I'M GLAD
I COULD REACH YOU.
NO ONE ELSE HAS
RESPONDED SO FAR.
- Natsu: YOU'RE
A VENTRILOQUIST?
- WOULD YOU KNOCK IT OFF?
AND KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
THE ENEMY HAS SCOUTS
THROUGHOUT THE WOODSEA.
THERE'S NO TELLING WHO
MIGHT BE LISTENING IN ON US.
THAT'S WHY I'M SPEAKING
DIRECTLY INTO YOUR HEAD.
PRETTY NEAT, HUH?
- ( groans )
- Hibiki: WHAT'S YOUR STATUS?
HAVE YOU FOUND WENDY
AND THE CAT?
- THEY'RE BOTH RIGHT HERE.
WENDY'S UNCONSCIOUS.
BUT HAPPY'S ALREADY WOKEN UP.
- Hibiki: THAT'S WONDERFUL.
NOW, HANG TIGHT.
I'M GONNA UPLOAD A MAP
INTO YOUR MIND.
IT'LL LEAD YOU STRAIGHT TO
THE TEMPORARY CAMP WE'VE SET UP.
I WAS GONNA SEND IT
TO THE CAT TOO,
BUT I CAN'T SEEM
TO MAKE A CONNECTION.
HE MUST BE RUNNING LOW
ON MAGIC POWER.
- HOLD ON, WHAT IS
THIS UPLOAD STUFF?
STAY OUT OF MY HEAD.
( gasps )
- NATSU, I THINK IT'S TIME
YOU SOUGHT PROFESSIONAL HELP.
- NOT NOW.
I HAVE TO FOLLOW THIS MAP
INSIDE MY BRAINS.
WOW, I CAN EVEN SEE
EXACTLY WHERE ERZA IS.
THIS UPLOAD STUFF IS COOL.
THANKS, GREAT TREE--
I MEAN, HIBIKI.
- Happy: AWW, MAN,
HE'S EVEN MORE FAR GONE
THAN I THOUGHT.
- PLEASE, HURRY.
I'M AFRAID THAT WE DON'T HAVE
THE LUXURY OF TIME RIGHT NOW.
- HEY, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND HOW NATSU
SUDDENLY KNEW
EXACTLY WHERE TO GO.
- I SENT HIM OUR LOCATION
USING ARCHIVE'S INFORMATION
COMPRESSION MAGIC.
IT PACKAGES THE INFORMATION
SO THAT IT CAN BE TRANSMITTED
AND SHARED WITH OTHERS
MUCH FASTER
THAN IT COULD BE VERBALLY.
- I HAD NO IDEA
THAT WAS EVEN POSSIBLE.
- MAGICALLY CONVERTING
AND TRANSMITTING DATA LIKE THIS
IS A FAIRLY NEW CONCEPT.
SO I WOULDN'T
EXPECT YOU TO KNOW.
- WOW, THAT'S REALLY IMPRESSIVE.
DID YOU HEAR THAT, ERZA?
WENDY'S GONNA BE HERE SOON.
JUST HOLD OUT
A LITTLE BIT LONGER, OKAY?
YOU CAN DO IT.
I MAY NOT BE
MUCH OF A FIGHTER,
BUT I'LL STAY HERE
TO PROTECT YOU.
PROMISE.
UM, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU SMILING AT?
DON'T YOU HAVE
SOME WORK TO DO?
- SORRY, I DIDN'T
MEAN ANYTHING BY IT.
IT'S JUST NICE TO SEE
SOME LIGHT IN THE DARKNESS.
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
GRAY'S STANDOFF
WITH RACER, THE LIGHTNING-FAST
MEMBER OF THE ORACION SEIS,
IS ABOUT TO ERUPT
INTO A VIOLENT BATTLE.
- I'M IMPRESSED, FAIRY TAIL.
NOBODY'S EVER
STOPPED ME TWICE.
TO SAVE FACE,
I'LL GIVE YOURS A THRASHING.
- OH, IS THAT SO?
- ONCE I LEAVE YOU IN THE DUST,
I CAN CATCH UP WITH
THAT FIRE-BREATHING BRAT
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE.
- HE'S SO FAST.
- BUT FIRST,
I GOT TO RUN YOU OVER!
I HAVE A FEELING IT WON'T
TAKE ME VERY LONG.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
( grunts )
- YOU THINK
YOU CAN STOP ME?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO PICK UP THE PACE.
- OH, MAN, HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIGHT THIS GUY?
( grunts )
- TELL YOU WHAT, ICE BOY--
I'LL LET YOU OFF THE HOOK
IF YOU JUST STAY ON THE GROUND.
THAT'S WHERE YOU BELONG, ANYWAY.
- OVER MY DEAD BODY.
- I CAN CERTAINLY
ARRANGE THAT FOR YOU.
LET'S KICK IT INTO OVERDRIVE!
DEAD GRAND PRIX!
- ( honking )
( engines whirr )
( motors run )
- WHAT IS THAT SOUND?
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
MAGI-CYCLES!
HOW MANY OF THEM ARE THERE?
I GOT TO PULL IT TOGETHER
BEFORE I GET RIPPED APART.
- ENJOYING MY
MOTOR SHOW FROM HELL?
- ( groans )
- HE'S PRETTY TOUGH.
- YOU'RE KIDDING?
YOU CAN ACTUALLY RIDE
THESE SCRAP HEAPS?
- WATCH YOUR MOUTH,
ICE BOY.
THESE SLEEK WONDERS ARE
ALMOST AS FAST AS I AM.
THEY'LL RUN CIRCLES
AROUND A CHUMP LIKE YOU.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A CHALLENGE TO ME.
( growls )
LOOK, THIS CHUMP
JUST TAMED A CHARGER.
- WELL, FANCY THAT.
- I SUPPOSE I SHOULD THANK YOU
FOR INCLUDING AN S.E. PLUG.
- Narrator: REMEMBER THESE?
AS WE'VE SEEN BEFORE,
THERE'RE MANY HANDY VEHICLES
IN THIS WORLD
THAT RUN ON MAGICAL ENERGY.
WHENEVER A WIZARD WANTS TO
OPERATE ONE OF THESE VEHICLES,
SAY A MAGIC MOBILE
OR A MAGI-CYCLE,
ALL THEY HAVE TO DO
IS CONNECT TO THE S.E. PLUG
AND THEIR MAGICAL ENERGY
WILL BE USED
TO POWER THE MACHINE'S ENGINE.
- IT'S GONNA BE TOUGH
HAVING THIS THING
CONSTANTLY SAPPING
MY MAGIC AWAY.
YOU AND ME, LET'S GO!
- OH, YEAH?! DO YOU
REALLY WANT TO RACE ME?
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- UNDERESTIMATE ME AND
YOU'LL BE EATING MY DUST, BUDDY.
- ( engines whirr )
- NICE.
I GOT TO SAY,
FOR A MEMBER OF
A PATHETICALLY WEAK GUILD,
YOU GOT SOME SHARP INSTINCTS.
- WHAT?! THAT'S IT!
NOW I'M ANGRY.
ICE MAKE: LANCE!
- MAYBE YOU'RE NOT
AS SHARP AS I THOUGHT.
- I'M STILL RIGHT
ON YOUR TAIL, MAN.
- MY TURN. HAVE FUN TRYING
TO DODGE THIS, FAIRY.
HIGH SIDE RUSH!
- HE'S THROWING TIRES!
- NOT TOO BAD, CHUMP.
NICE WARM UP.
NOW THE DEAD GRAND PRIX
CAN REALLY START.
( grunts )
IT'S THE END OF THE LINE!
- CLOSE CALL. THIS GUY'S
GOT SOME GEARS LOOSE.
- WHAT'S UP?
TOO INTENSE FOR YOU?
- ( gasps )
- ( rumbling )
- I'VE GOT TO PROTECT ERZA.
I'M NOT GONNA
LOSE TO THIS FREAK.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
CAUSED THAT EXPLOSION?
- GRAY, NATSU, PICK ONE.
- ( engine whirrs )
- Sherry: THAT GUY'S WITH
THE ORACION SEIS, RIGHT?
- Lyon: YES,
THE ONE CALLED RACER.
- LYON!
- GRAY?
- YOU'RE TIMING COULDN'T
BE ANY BETTER, MAN.
HOP ABOARD.
- EXCUSE ME?
- YOU HEARD ME,
SO LET'S GO.
- ( engine revs )
- BUT, LYON--
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
YOU STAY HERE ON STANDBY.
- SURE, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- ( engine runs )
- WHAT EXACTLY
DOES THAT ENTAIL?
- GRAY, DID YOU FIND WENDY?
- YEAH, AND HAPPY.
NATSU'S GOT BOTH OF THEM.
- GOOD, SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
- I NEED YOU TO HELP ME
TAKE CARE OF THIS SPEED FREAK.
IT'S NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE
TO CAST SPELLS
WHILE I'M DRIVING THIS THING.
- OH?
SO YOU'RE SAYING
YOU CAN'T DO THIS WITHOUT ME.
VERY WELL, I'LL SHOW YOU
SOME REAL ICE MAKE MAGIC.
- JUST SHUT UP AND DO IT.
- HERE IT GOES!
HOW PATHETIC.
YOU STILL USE TWO HANDS
WHEN CASTING YOUR
ICE MAKE SPELLS.
- LYON, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU NEVER CAST
WITH TWO HANDS.
- THAT IS WHAT
UR TAUGHT US, RIGHT?
ICE MAKE: EAGLE!
- NICE, HE'S DOWN.
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
- YOU'RE GONNA PAY
FOR TRASHING MY RIDE.
- Both: NOW, ICE MAKE...
- APE!
- HAMMER!
- THAT'S SOME QUICK
MAKER MAGIC YOU GUYS GOT THERE.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO MOVE
WAY FASTER THAN THAT.
- ( grunts )
- JUST GIVE IT UP!
- ( groans )
- IF YOU WANT TO LAND
A HIT ON ME,
YOU'LL HAVE TO BE
FASTER THAN LIGHTNING.
- THIS IS POINTLESS.
- DON'T LOSE YOUR COOL, GRAY.
HE'S COMING IN
AT FOUR O'CLOCK.
TOGETHER WE CAN STOP HIM.
WE JUST NEED TO FOCUS.
- GOT TO KEEP COOL, HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
SO LET'S DO THIS!
- FIRE WHEN I GIVE THE WORD
AND DON'T YOU
DARE HOLD BACK.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
WHY ARE THEY
TAKING OFF THEIR CLOTHES?
- OH, WOW,
LYON'S STRIPPING TOO.
IT MUST BE OUT OF LOVE.
- Lyon: THERE!
HE'S IN FRONT OF US
AND HEADED THIS WAY!
- WE'VE GOT YOU NOW.
ICE GEYSER!
- SNOW DRAGON!
- NO WAY.
- HE'S EVEN FASTER THAN BEFORE.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, PUNKS?
- CAN'T KEEP UP?
- YOU COULD ATTACK ME
FOR ETERNITY
AND YOU'D NEVER COME CLOSE
TO LANDING A SINGLE HIT.
REMEMBER, YOU'RE DEALING
WITH THE FASTEST MAN ALIVE.
- OH NO, ARE ALL THE REST
OF THEM THIS POWERFUL?
- BEEN FUN, BUT IT'S TIME
FOR THE FINAL
THRASHING TO BEGIN.
I'LL MAKE IT AS QUICK
AND PAINFUL AS POSSIBLE.
- DON'T WORRY, GRAY.
WE'VE WON.
I JUST FIGURED OUT HOW WE'RE
GONNA BEAT THIS GUY.
- Makarov: THE INVESTIGATION
REPORT HAS COME IN.
- REGARDING THE ORACION SEIS?
- YES, IT SEEMS THE FELLOW
CALLING HIMSELF "BRAIN"
MIGHT HAVE WORKED
FOR THE BUREAU OF
MAGICAL DEVELOPMENT.
- FOR THE BUREAU?
DO THEY KNOW HIS IDENTITY?
- THEY'RE LOOKING INTO IT
AS WE SPEAK.
WHAT'S EVEN MORE TROUBLING
IS THIS R-SYSTEM
THE REPORT MENTIONED.
IT APPARENTLY HAS TIES
TO THAT MONSTROSITY,
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
WILL WE NEVER
LEAVE ITS SHADOW?
- THAT MEANS IT'S CONNECTED
TO JELLAL IN SOME WAY.
IS BRAIN CONTINUING HIS WORK?
- HMM.
THAT'S DEFINITELY
A POSSIBILITY.
IF HE IS FOLLOWING
JELLAL'S FOOTSTEPS,
THE WORLD AS WE KNOW IT
COULD BE IN GRAVE DANGER.
- IT'LL BE OKAY, MASTER.
- HMM?
- FAIRY TAIL'S STRONGEST TEAM
IS OUT THERE.
THAT FACT ALONE KEEPS
ALL OF MY DOUBTS AT BAY.
- WELL SAID, MIRA.
- LET'S JUST HOPE
THEY DON'T DESTROY
HALF OF THE WORLD
THEY'RE TRYING TO PROTECT.
- YOU KIDS ARE GONNA
DRIVE ME TO AN EARLY GRAVE.
- I WONDER WHAT THOSE TWO
COULD BE WHISPERING ABOUT.
- HUH, STRATEGIZE ALL YOU WANT.
IT WON'T DO YOU ANY GOOD.
- AND IF ALL GOES WELL,
WE GOT HIM.
- ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
- TOO BAD, THAT'S THE PLAN.
I'LL STOP HIM WITHOUT YOU.
- WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET ME GO!
- WHY ARE YOU
FREEZING HIM LIKE THAT?
- Gray: WILL YOU QUIT
SCREWING AROUND?!
YOU CAN'T TAKE THIS GUY
BY YOURSELF AND YOU KNOW IT!
- HA, JUST SIT BACK
AND ENJOY THE SHOW.
I'LL FINISH HIM.
- MAN, THAT WAS
KIND OF HARSH.
IS THAT HOW YOU
TREAT YOUR FRIENDS?
- IF YOU THINK
THE TWO OF US ARE FRIENDS,
THEN YOU'RE SORELY MISTAKEN.
WE SIMPLY STUDIED
UNDER THE SAME MASTER
WHEN WE WERE YOUNG.
THAT WAS ALL.
- OH YEAH?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WE'LL NEED HIS HELP.
- WE CAN HANDLE HIM
ON OUR OWN.
TOGETHER, WE WILL
GIVE LAMIA SCALE
ITS GREATEST VICTORY EVER.
NOW LET'S GET TO WORK.
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
- I'D BE CAREFUL
IF I WERE YOU.
LET YOUR ARROGANCE
GET THE BEST OF YOU,
AND YOU'RE SURE TO LOSE.
HA, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
EVER HAD A CHANCE
OF BEATING ME, ANYWAY, RIGHT?
- NOW WHO'S BEING ARROGANT?
- MARIONETTE ATTACK!
ROCK DOLL!
- THAT'S A NEAT TRICK, GIRLIE,
BUT IT'S TOO SLOW
TO CATCH ME.
- IT'S PRACTICALLY
STANDING STILL.
- I CAN'T EVEN SEE HIM.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
GO, WOOD DOLL!
- YEAH, KEEP THROWING
THEM MY WAY.
IT'S TOTALLY POINTLESS.
- I WOULDN'T BE
SO SURE IF I WERE YOU.
- ( groans )
YOU GOT ME.
- THERE'S NO WAY
HE BROKE FREE.
( screams )
- TOLD YOU, SWEETHEART!
- OVER HERE, SLOWPOKE.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING AT, PAL.
THE ONLY SLOWPOKE
HERE IS YOU.
- YOUR SPEED COUNTS FOR NOTHING
IF YOUR ATTACKS HAVE
NO POWER BEHIND THEM.
I CAN PROVE YOU
LACK THE ABILITY
TO LAND A DECISIVE BLOW.
- OH YEAH?
- LET'S SEE HOW YOU HANDLE THIS.
ICE MAKE: HEDGEHOG!
BETTER NOT GET TOO CLOSE OR
YOU'LL END UP A SHISH KABOB.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, RACER?
ARE YOU AFRAID THAT
BELOVED SPEED OF YOURS
MIGHT GET YOU SKEWERED?
- DON'T GET COCKY, KID.
GEAR CHANGE: RED ZONE!
YOU'RE SO NAIVE.
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK
I'D USE MY FULL SPEED
FROM THE GET-GO AGAINST
SUCH A WEAK OPPONENT?
- COME GET ME!
- YOU'RE ON!
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
- ( grunts, pants )
( grunts )
- ( pants )
PLEASE, HANG ON, LYON.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT HAPPENED TO
ALL THAT BRAVADO?
- ( screams )
- WOW, THAT KID MUST BE
A GLUTTON FOR PUNISHMENT.
- WHERE IS HE
RUNNING OFF TO NOW?
- ICE MAKE: EAGLE!
- WHEN ARE YOU GONNA REALIZE,
YOU CAN'T HIT ME?
DON'T TELL ME
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT.
MAN, WHAT A WASTE OF SPACE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ALL
THE BIG TALK FROM BEFORE?
YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE
I DON'T HAVE THE POWER
TO LAND A DECISIVE BLOW?
WHY DON'T I SHOW YOU?
I DON'T NEED THAT POWER
TO PUT THE BRAKES ON THIS FIGHT.
AS QUICK AS I AM,
I COULD EASILY
TAKE YOU OUT BEFORE
YOU COULD EVEN THINK
ABOUT USING ANY
SORT OF FANCY MAGIC.
I MEAN, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
YOU'VE GOT SERIOUS SKILLS, KID.
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN FINE
IF YOU'D NEVER
CROSSED PATHS WITH ME.
BUT I'M ONE OF
THE ORACION SEIS.
- ( gull squawks )
- SIX DEMONS,
SIX PRAYERS,
SIX UNWAVERING PILLARS,
AND ANYONE WHO
TRIES TO CUT US OFF
WILL PAY THE FINAL TOLL
FOR THEIR DISRESPECT.
SO SAY GOOD-BYE.
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
I FIGURED OUT THE TRUTH
BEHIND YOUR MAGIC
WHILE GRAY AND I
WERE FIGHTING TOGETHER.
I LOOKED UP AND NOTICED
THE BIRDS IN THE DISTANCE,
WERE FLYING INCREDIBLY FAST.
- ( gulps )
- YOU WERE NEVER
AS FAST AS LIGHTNING.
YOU JUST ALTERED OUR
PERCEPTION OF SPEED,
SO IT WOULD SEEM THAT WAY.
YOU SLOWED US DOWN,
THAT'S ALL.
ONCE I GOT OUTSIDE
THE PERIMETER OF YOUR MAGIC,
I REALIZED WHAT
WAS GOING ON.
DESPITE YOUR NAME,
YOU'RE JUST AS SLOW
AS THE REST OF US.
I THOUGHT IT'D BE
HARDER TO DEFEAT YOU.
BUT NOW THAT YOU'VE FOLLOWED ME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE,
GRAY IS OUTSIDE
THE PERIMETER OF YOUR MAGIC
AND CAN TAKE YOU DOWN.
- ( gasps )
- Lyon: HE SHOULD HAVE
A CLEAR SHOT FROM UP THERE.
- WAIT, SO YOU TWO
WEREN'T ARGUING.
YOU WERE GIVING HIM
A SNIPING POST.
- NOW THIS IS MORE LIKE IT.
FRESH AIR AND
A STATIONARY TARGET.
- THERE'S NO WAY
HE'LL HIT ME FROM THERE.
HE'S OVER A MILE AWAY.
- OH, HE CAN DO IT.
IF THERE'S ONE THING
THAT I'VE LEARNED,
IT'S TO NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
A MEMBER OF
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
THERE'S NO STOPPING THEM.
- HERE GOES
SUPER FREEZING...
ARROW!
- IT'S SO FAST!
MY PRAYER...
TO BE FAST.
FASTER THAN ANYONE ELSE.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
- Gray: I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT ACTUALLY WORKED.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THERE ARE FIVE MORE
JUST AS STRONG AS HIM.
- ON ANOTHER NOTE,
COULD YOU PLEASE
TRY TO INCLUDE ME
IN YOUR LITTLE RUSE,
NEXT TIME?
- DON'T BLAME ME.
HE'S THE MAN WITH THE PLAN.
- THANKS.
- CAN YOU STAND UP?
- I THINK I'LL SIT
A BIT LONGER.
- ( giggles )
- I'VE GOT YOU NOW!
IN THE NAME OF
THE MIGHTY ORACION SEIS,
I'M TAKING YOU
TO THE BIG SLAB IN THE SKY!
- ( slow beeping )
- Lyon: IS THAT WHAT
I THINK IT IS?
- HE'S RIGGED HIMSELF
WITH A BOMB LACRIMA.
- SERIOUSLY? IS HE INSANE?
- WE'LL CROSS
THE FINISH LINE TOGETHER.
- NO WAY.
( grunts )
- ( laughs )
- IT'S NO USE.
I'M ON EMPTY.
WE'RE TOTALLY SCREWED!
- ( grunts )
- ( fast beeping )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- NO, LYON.
- ( beeping )
- GRAY...
I ALWAYS KNEW YOU'D
BE THE DEATH OF ME.
- Sherry: NO!
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING!
THERE'S NO WAY
HE'S GONE!
- LYON!
- ( groans )
RACER'S STRUCK DOWN?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW COULD ONE OF
THE ORACION SEIS
BE DEFEATED LIKE THIS?
NO, IT SEEMS I HAVE
UNDERESTIMATED OUR ADVERSARIES.
I NEVER IMAGINED
I WOULD BE FORCED
TO SEND HIM.
WAKE UP, MIDNIGHT.
YOU HAVE WORK TO DO.
- ( groans )
- FIND OUR FOES AND TOSS
THEM INTO YOUR NIGHTMARE.
- ( end theme playing )
- YES, FATHER.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: MAN, I'M JEALOUS.
I WISH I COULD BREATHE FIRE
LIKE YOU, NATSU.
- Natsu: WHY? YOU WANT TO FRY
BADDIES TOO?
- NO, TO FRY FISH, DUMMY.
AND LIGHT UP ANY DARK PLACES
I MIGHT CRAWL INTO.
- WHY DON'T YOU TRY
EATING SOME OF MY FIRE?
I MEAN, IT WORKS FOR ME.
GO AHEAD, EAT UP.
- NAH, I'LL PASS.
HOT FOODS
TEND TO GIVE ME HEARTBURN.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu: COME ON, JUST TRY SOME.
WHO KNOWS,
MAYBE CARLA WILL LIKE YOU
IF YOU CAN BREATHE FIRE.
- YOU THINK SO?
OKAY, DOWN THE HATCH.
- PLOP.
- Happy: ( screams )