[NARRATOR] Determined to
rebuild the Fairy Tail Guild,
Natsu, Happy, and Lucy
set out on a mission
to track down all
their old friends.
They located Wendy and Carla,
who were now members of
Lyon's guild, Lamia Scale.
However, there was a catch.
[YUKA] The Sky Sisters!
Shelia and Wendy!
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH scream]
I'm a member of the
Lamia Scale guild now.
I can't just walk
away with you.
[BOTH gasp]
So you shouldn't stick around
because you feel sorry for me.
I want you to do what
makes you happy.
[OROCHI TAMER]
Tonight, the hammer of judgment
will fall squarely
upon Lamia Scale.
Soon the streets will be
running red with blood.
[SHELIA] They're so obsessed
with attacking our guild,
they don't even care how many
innocent people get hurt.
'Cause I'm fired up now!
Let's go, Happy!
Aye, aye, to the sky!
Sorry about that, Natsu!
[NATSU]
Move it!
That's insane.
[TOBY] He's more of a monster
than the dang monsters!
[CARLA]
There are so many of them.
[HAPPY]
So scary!
And they're all
heading towards town!
Lyon and the rest of the guild
can hold them off for a while.
Natsu and Lucy will help, too.
Our mission is clear.
A focused strike.
We're going to neutralize
that monster tamer.
Sorry about this, Happy.
Don't worry. I don't have
any problem carrying you.
You're not heavy like Lucy.
[LUCY growls]
That's not what I mean.
It's just... I wasn't
gonna stand back
when I knew I could
do something to help.
I feel the same.
Kinda funny, don't you think?
[WENDY]
Hm?
We were fighting on opposite
sides when we first met.
But now, we're both on the same
team protecting Lamia Scale.
Because of you.
After the match, you said
that we should be friends.
[SHELIA]
Mh-mh.
Still, we wouldn't be together
right now if you had said no.
[SHELIA yelps]
[WENDY gasps]
[WENDY]
Oh my goodness!
You're not injured, are you?
[WENDY yelps]
[CROWD laughing, clapping]
Hi. I'm Wendy.
It's nice to meet you.
[laughs]
Yeah, same to you.
Dragon Slayer Secret Art!
Shattering Light...
...Sky Drill!
[SHELIA yells]
You're really somethin' else!
That was so fun!
Hey, listen.
I don't hate fighting,
but I don't love it either.
It's just gonna
get worse for you
if ya keep dragging this out,
'cause it's obvious
I'm gonna win.
I don't need your pity.
I'm not giving up, so
please, come and get me!
Beat me until I fall
to the ground!
Can you do that?
She came at me full force
so I gotta do the same.
'Cause that's love!
Gathering Clouds of Heaven!
Sky Dragon Crushing Fang!
[bell ringing]
[chuckles]
That was a lotta fun.
Here ya go.
[WENDY sighs]
Feels good!
Weird as it sounds, I kinda
had a lotta fun, too.
Let's be friends from now on.
Whaddaya say?
[WENDY]
Mh-hm!
I'd love to! Yeah!
Look there!
[HAPPY]
Uh! I don't see him!
[SHELIA]
I do! Let's get a little closer!
[HAPPY]
Aye, Sir!
Who's that?
[WENDY, SHEILA]
Sky Sisters attack!
Sky Dragon...
And Sky God...
[WENDY]
...Roar!
[SHELIA]
...Howl!
[OROCHI MEMBERS screaming]
What in the hell is
wrong with you?
They're just two little girls!
[CARLA] You should
really learn to count!
[CARLA]
White Moon!
[HAPPY]
Whoa...
Carla.
[grunting]
I guess it's time for
me to show them
what I've been training for.
Oh, just go and
hide somewhere!
[yells]
[ALL yell]
[gasps]
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
[OROCHI MEMBERS scream]
I'll go take out
the monster tamer!
Okay. But promise
you'll careful!
[SHELIA] I can't let
the horde reach the city!
Sky God Dance!
[OROCHI MEMBERS scream]
[OROCHI MEMBERS yelling]
Wait a minute.
I know that smell.
[NATSU yelling]
[MONSTERS roaring]
[NATSU]
Outta my way!
[MONSTERS groaning]
All right, ya thief!
I'm comin' for ya!
[MONSTERS roaring]
Ready?
[TOBY, YUKA]
Yeah!
Let's do this!
Now, open Gate of the Lion!
Loke!
Your knight in shining
armor is here.
[LUCY]
Star Dress!
It's Leo fashion.
So cool!
Just like Erza!
Requip spell?
It's actually a
little different.
You look radiant
in that, Lucy!
When I summon
a celestial spirit,
I can use some of
their magic myself.
Just lovely!
Cut it out.
But this means I'm able to
jump into the fight, as well!
In a dress?
She's amazing, isn't she?
Glad to have you by our side.
[MONSTERS roaring]
[LYON]
Ice Make...
...Eagle!
Here I go!
Ultra-Poison Nails:
Mega-Mega Jellyfish!
[TOBY yelling]
[YUKA]
Wave!
Ha!
I'll spin you, puppy!
Regulus Impact!
[yells]
Regulus Lucy... Kick!
Seriously?!
It's a light-based attack,
to be specific.
Sky Dragon Talon!
Now Sky God... Boreas!
[OROCHI MEMBERS screaming]
[SHELIA]
Where did that monster tamer go?
There he is!
Say goodbye!
Watch out, Shelia!
You saved me.
[BLUENOTE]
Shall I step in?
No, no.
These pests are not worth
the sweat off your brow.
[BLUENOTE]
Huh?
Are you okay?
Think so.
[BLUENOTE] That girl. I've
seen her somewhere before.
Wait. You sure?
I want to see how
you "fly" now.
[BOTH scream]
What's going on?
[HAPPY]
Uh! The ground blew up!
[HAPPY screams]
No. It's him again.
Oh, dear.
That's Bluenote Stinger.
He's from Grimoire Heart.
[BLUENOTE]
Hm?
[gasps]
I can't move!
Something's holding us down!
[BLUENOTE]
With the power of my gravity,
I can squash you
all like insects.
Sir, please, I beg you
to exercise restraint.
You're crushing my men as well.
[BLUENOTE growls]
[OROCHI TAMER] Never mind.
Forget I said anything.
Feel free to do
whatever you want, sir.
I don't get it. Why is he here?
[BLUENOTE]
Black hole!
Ready? Let's fly!
Where to begin?
Shelia!
Gotcha!
[SHELIA gasps]
Natsu!
You made it!
He can stand?
It's like the gravity
doesn't affect him!
What's the big idea
with stealin' Happy?
I'm sorry about that.
Natsu, this isn't the
time for such nonsense.
Do you see who we're fighting?
It's the guy who nearly
killed us on Tenrou Island!
That's Bluenote Stinger!
[NATSU]
Hm?
[grumbles]
Never seen him before.
Seriously?!
[BLUENOTE]
He's familiar as well.
Fairy Glitter? Fat chance!
Agh! I'm a human pancake!
Fire Dragon Roar!
[NATSU screams]
[BLUENOTE]
Cocky little brat!
He was nothing but a pest.
But still, seeing his face
and hearing his voice
fills me with rage!
Whoa! His power is intense!
I can barely move.
It's crazy. How strong is he?
Bluenote, sir!
[BLUENOTE]
I need to take him out. Quickly!
I'll crush you!
[NATSU]
You're not crushin' anyone!
[SHELIA screams]
Look at that fire!
It's lifting the ground!
No way!
[NATSU] You shoulda never
messed with Fairy Tail!
[BLUENOTE]
Fairy Tail?
That's it!
That's how I know them!
'Cause now you're gonna pay!
[BLUENOTE]
Black... Hole!
This one can really "fly"!
[gasping]
[OROCHI N gasps]
[OROCHI MEMBERS gasp]
[groaning]
[CARLA]
Just one attack?
[WENDY]
My goodness.
He's only trained a year and
he's gotten this much stronger?
[SHELIA yelping]
Come on, you know not to steal.
[SHELIA] More importantly,
my clothes are on fire!
[HAPPY] Hey, Natsu, forget
about the lecture for now.
Look over there.
[NATSU]
Uh?
[HAPPY] The bad guys
are doin' somethin'.
[OROCHI TAMER]
We surrender.
[YUKA] Looks like the monsters
were all turned away.
[TOBY grunting]
Way to go, guys!
Well, of course we won.
Thanks to you,
Marguerite is safe again.
I still wanna smash stuff.
I'm sure we're just gettin'
started, 'ol buddy.
It's kinda hard to
believe Orochi Fin
hired Bluenote Stinger.
They hired who, now?
Wait! The gravity guy?
You really didn't remember him?
[LUCY]
I understand why you'd forget.
We got attacked by something
way more powerful than
him right afterward.
Huh. I don't know
what you mean.
I guess it must be my
turn to forget stuff.
She means Acnologia.
[LUCY] Oh. So, you can
remember his name.
There's a good reason
I can't forget him.
[roars]
[gasps]
Do you happen to know where
Wendy and Shelia ran off to?
Those young ladies
are both gonna be
beautiful women before too long.
[YUKA]
They needed to talk in private.
So much for my plan.
Huh? What does that mean?
I just wanted to prove to
you that I would be able
to handle things all on my own.
That you don't need to worry.
But then, Natsu went and
messed the whole thing up.
That's kinda what
he's known for.
Listen, Wendy, you need to go
and be by Natsu's side again.
[WENDY]
What?
[SHELIA]
You love him, don't you?
Hold on! You're making it
sound like something else.
I mean, I do look up to him,
sure. But it's way different.
He's more like my big brother.
You know, that's love, too.
[SHELIA] If you don't
go, you'll regret it.
It's obvious Natsu
still believes in you.
And in Fairy Tail.
He has a lot of love for you.
And Fairy Tail's a
guild built on love;
it's what brings you together.
Yeah, but...
[SHELIA]
Follow your heart.
Wendy, even if we're
in different guilds,
you and I will
always be friends.
You mean it?
[SHELIA]
Mh-hm.
Friends forever.
[WENDY] Thanks so much for
everything you've done!
It was a pleasure to have you.
[CARLA] We truly
appreciate your kindness.
And we appreciate your help.
I'm sorry. I feel
terrible about leaving.
Like I'm... just being selfish.
This was what we agreed
to when you joined,
so don't be sad.
[NATSU]
It was?
We always said we'd be
part of their guild
until Fairy Tail re-formed.
Don't go, Carla!
We'll miss you.
I know.
Jeez. Pull yourself
together, child.
[LUCY] Even though they
joined another guild,
I'm so happy that they
never gave up on Fairy Tail.
Come on, don't be
such a crybaby.
I'm sorry.
It'll be all right.
I can take over as one
of the Sky Sisters
so the show can go on.
In your dreams.
Leave it to me!
[LAMIA D, LAMIA E]
It's never gonna happen!
[LYON] Farewell, and best of
luck with rebuilding Fairy Tail.
[NATSU]
Thanks!
[LYON]
Give Gray my regards.
Ya know, he's one
of the members
I've completely lost track of.
Careful out there!
So long.
Bye, Wendy! I'll miss you!
Bye! I'll miss you, too!
Hey. It's okay to cry.
But I won't.
Fairy Tail is getting
back together
and that's nothing to cry about.
That's quite enough
tears for now, Wendy.
Dry your eyes.
I know.
But they were so sweet
after Fairy Tail broke up.
I really started to feel like
I was becoming part
of a family again,
then you guys came back for me.
[LUCY] She's crying because
she's sad and happy?
This is only the
start of it, Wendy!
We're gonna get everybody
back together!
Yeah!
So, where are heading
off to next?
Good question.
[LUCY]
Well, if we travel eastward,
we'll reach a place called
Rain Bringer Village.
[WENDY]
That's a kind of a weird name.
[LUCY] Supposedly, it never
stops raining there,
so I'd say it's pretty fitting.
[HAPPY] We know someone
who likes the rain.
[LUCY] The search for the Fairy
Tail members continues
in Rain Bringer Village,
where we find a broken-hearted
Juvia, all alone.
She tell us about what
Gray has been up to.
And it reminds Natsu
about something
he learned about a year ago.
Something we need to stop.
A shadow is looming over Gray.
If it grows, his heart and soul
could be lost to the
darkness forever.
Next Time: "Avatar."
With the dark guilds gone,
evil is making a new
home in the kingdom.