[gasps]
You're lying!
[IRENE]
No, it's true.
I was known as the
"Queen of Dragons."
I shall tell you a story
about events that took
place 400 years ago
in a kingdom here on
Ishgar, called "Dragnof."
Hear about the
western continent?
There was another attack.
By the dragons?
[BOTH gasp]
That doesn't surprise me.
Dragons in the west
are uncivilized brutes.
[SOLDIER A]
Sage Dragon Belserion!
[SOLDIER B] Glad to see you've
returned unharmed, sir.
The situation there
is worse than imagined.
Things are dire.
I need to see Irene.
Right! Her Majesty is
here, in the courtyard.
[BELSERION]
Irene.
Belserion. So good to see you.
[IRENE]
What's the matter? Are you ill?
[BELSERION]
I come bearing bad news.
The dragons in the west
show no signs of relenting.
It's only a matter of time
before they've consumed
all the humans and
come to Ishgar.
How ghastly.
They're eating people.
Unbelievable.
Just the thought of it
alone... It's blasphemy.
In Ishgar, we see our
relationship with humans
as invaluable.
[IRENE]
Likewise.
I can't imagine where
our society would be
without the dragons' help.
Our species can peacefully
coexist, but one has to wonder:
If the western dragons' way of
thinking reaches our shores
and begins to take root,
would that place our
bond in jeopardy?
[BELSERION]
We will not allow it.
On our honor,
we'll protect humankind!
[IRENE] This marked the
beginning of the bloody war
that would later be known as
the "Dragon King Festival."
Yes.
Ironically, it was first sparked
by the kindness of dragons.
[ERZA]
Four hundred years ago?
How have you not aged?
[IRENE]
I'll address that eventually.
You should like this next part,
so listen well, okay?
In fact, I think your little
Dragon Slayer friend
will hang on every word.
[WENDY]
Huh?
[IRENE] My kingdom was
a place of harmony,
with humans and dragons
living together
in peace for generations.
Back then, several such
kingdoms existed in Ishgar.
[CROWD gasps]
She broke an iron sword
with a wooden stick!
Your Majesty, how'd you do it?
With imbuement magic.
I call it "enchantment."
Nice, huh?
To put it simply,
I enhanced the wooden stick.
The enchantment made it
harder than the iron.
[CIVILIAN B]
That's amazing!
We could use this spell to make
our dragons' scales
even tougher!
This is our chance
to win the war!
[IRENE] However, things
did not go in our favor.
The sheer number of
dragons from the west
dwarfed those on our side.
Plus, there were some in Ishgar
who chose to ally themselves
with those seeking to disrupt
our peaceful coexistence.
[BELSERION]
Irene.
Belserion.
We're losing.
[IRENE]
I see. Are you sure?
My wish for peace
remains steadfast.
I won't give up.
Know this, no matter how
many brethren I lose,
I'll still fight.
I don't understand.
Why make such a sacrifice?
Why? I've told you how
your predecessor saved me.
This is my debt to pay.
[IRENE]
I knew that,
but surely that debt has
been long since repaid.
You've devoted your life
to serving not only me,
but all of mankind,
yet you're willing to give more.
Listen, my debt
will not be repaid
till you are forever safe.
To that end,
I'll pledge my life.
[IRENE]
Belserion.
Let me join you
and fight by your side.
You can't be serious.
We're up against
dragons, not people!
You won't survive,
not even with an army.
They'll destroy you!
[IRENE] I've found a way we
can win, a new technique.
[IRENE] But it's only possible
if I can imbue myself
with your power.
Will you allow it?
The power of a dragon
within a human?
We can create a whole
new class of wizards...
...able to fight dragons.
Called Dragon Slayers.
[gasps]
[ERZA] Are you trying to say you
created that type of magic?
[IRENE]
I am saying it.
You can consider me to be
the mother of Dragon Slayers.
It's not working.
He's not getting warmer.
Please, Natsu, wake up!
Come on. I know you're
still in there somewhere.
Natsu!
[NATSU]
Hm?
[gasps]
Do you remember Anna
telling us a long time ago
about who created
Dragon Slayer magic?
It was somebody named Irene.
What's goin' on?
When'd you get here? Hm?
This is your mind, ya know,
so quit bein' so shocked.
You guys really piss me
off sometimes!
I thought you were
supposed to be tellin' me
why I'm on the verge
of death or somethin'!
Not our fault.
All we're supposed
to do is lead you down
some kinda path through
your memories.
We're almost to the
end, Natsu! Come on!
Natsu.
Don't die.
[IRENE] After producing
numerous Dragon Slayers,
we were able to gain the
upper hand in the war.
Victory seemed to
be within reach,
and with that victory,
came our very survival.
[SLAYER B yells]
[SLAYER A roars]
[IRENE]
However, the great potential
that had been unlocked
began to take its toll on
the bodies wielding it.
Those unable to suppress this
wellspring of power went mad.
The extraordinary sensory
perception of dragons
caused extreme vertigo and
motion sickness in humans.
[IRENE]
What's more...
[SOLDIER A]
Excuse me, Your Majesty?
Your face... What's wrong?
[IRENE]
Huh?
[IRENE] Inside those who'd
gained this new power
grew Dragon Seeds.
[IRENE] These "seeds"
would turn those people
into dragons, spelling
doom for any Dragon Slayer.
[IRENE] To complicate things
further, at that time,
I was carrying a
child in my womb.
You, Erza.
[IRENE] I'm sure you're
curious about your father.
He was a general of a
neighboring country.
Our marriage was
political in nature.
A "solution" to a
territorial dispute.
Can you make it?
Yes!
[DRAGON A roars]
The Dragon Slayers'
power is incredible.
It borders on supernatural.
[IRENE]
No!
I'm done. This is the
end of my journey.
[IRENE]
Belserion!
Irene, I've failed my
duty to protect you.
I've failed to preserve our
peaceful coexistence.
[IRENE crying]
[IRENE] Your father fought by
my side on many battlefields,
and was there to comfort me
as I watched Belserion die.
[IRENE] When Acnologia
rose up, the war ended
with neither side coming
away as the clear victor.
As if ridiculing the countless
lives that were lost,
Acnologia, alone,
stood victorious.
[IRENE] Then, just one week
after the fighting stopped...
[RUNG]
You monster! I'll kill you!
Stay back!
[IRENE]
It's me! Irene!
Be patient. I know
I can fix this!
Please, Rung!
Careful. She'll end up
just like Acnologia!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
No, please! I won't!
I would never choose
to harm the dragons.
[grunts]
[RUNG] That means you're
an enemy of humankind.
[IRENE gasps]
Seize her, men!
We must lock up this dragon
woman for our own safety!
[IRENE]
Stop! Listen to me!
I'm carrying your child!
[RUNG gasps]
What did she say?
If that's true,
then that must mean...
The child is cursed.
[RUNG growls]
I would never father a child
with a monster like you!
[gasps]
After that, my life
became a living hell,
filled only with misery.
Torture, beatings,
dehumanization.
[IRENE]
And then...
Don't worry.
I'll do everything in my power
to keep you safe from harm.
[footsteps]
[RUNG]
Dragon woman,
the day of your execution
has been decided.
That's fine.
But please!
Please spare my child!
I've had enough of
this foolishness!
No child takes three
years to be born!
[IRENE] That's because
I cast a spell on it.
I can't have it here,
not in this hellish place!
There is no child!
To prove it, I'll split
open your belly myself!
[IRENE]
No! Don't! I'm begging you!
No!
See? You're just like Acnologia.
A blight on humanity!
[IRENE snarls]
No! You monste--!
Wait! What was that?
It's coming from the dungeon!
[SOLDIER F] Let's move!
We have to save General Rung!
[SOLDIER G]
Hurry!
[ALL gasp]
[IRENE snarls]
[SOLDIER D]
A dragon?
[SOLDIER E]
It must be that dragon woman!
[SOLDIER C] You'll pay
for killing the general!
[IRENE]
This can't be happening.
I know I'm still a human!
I don't want this!
I wanna be a person again!
Somebody, please. Help me!
[IRENE]
Centuries passed,
and during all that time,
I carried you inside me, Erza.
My child.
I lived deep in the mountains,
far away from human
civilization,
searching for a way
to lift this curse.
[roars]
[IRENE]
Then, one day...
[ZEREF]
Do my eyes deceive me?
It's been ages since
I've last seen a dragon.
Who're you?
No. You're actually
a human, aren't you?
[IRENE]
On that day, I met His Majesty.
His magic ability
was unparalleled.
In the blink of an eye,
he cured the affliction that
had plagued me for centuries.
[IRENE gasping]
Human!
I can hardly believe it.
Oh! I'm back.
I'm human!
This is merely an appearance.
You'll never truly return
to who you once were.
[IRENE] It's okay.
I can live with that.
I'm so happy!
Just looking like my old
self after all this time
fills my heart with joy.
[IRENE] However, soon I
discovered the shortcomings
of my new condition.
There's no flavor.
[IRENE]
I gorged myself sick.
But I couldn't taste anything.
[IRENE coughing]
So tired. God, all I want
is to fall asleep, please.
[IRENE] This pain.
I'm so itchy. And so cold.
What's happening to me?
Why won't it stop?
I just wanna live
like a normal human.
[ZEREF]
This is merely an appearance.
You'll never be human.
I'm not some kind of monster!
I'm human! I'm human!
[IRENE] I don't want my
baby to suffer as I have.
I want it to be human.
Human.
Growing inside me... is a human.
[IRENE]
I'm carrying a human life.
With a human body...
[IRENE]
...could be a new beginning.
I can enchant myself
into this child.
Then I would have
a human body.
It would be just like before.
Oh...
I'd be a new being.
In a new body, I would
have a new chance at life!
I will be you,
and you will be me!
Come, my child, let us
join and become one!
[IRENE]
Alas, it didn't work.
Enchanting myself into the child
was an impossible dream.
Since I had no use for
you, I threw you away.
So you wouldn't weigh me down.
I simply left you in some
backwater hamlet.
[ERZA]
And that was Rosemary Village?
I didn't care to
remember the name.
Erza.
It's all right.
Guess I should thank you.
If only for giving me
the gift of life.
A waste of breath.
Your life was no
gift, I promise.
What's wrong with you?!
She's your own child!
[ERZA]
You may be right.
Leaving me behind
was the true gift.
If you hadn't thrown me away,
I may have never
met my real family!
[LUCY] Now, Erza has finally
learned the secret
behind her birth from
her biological mother.
Despite this harsh truth,
she remains unfazed.
The memories of meeting
her dear friends
and everything they've
shared together
make it clear where
her allegiance lies.
And so, Fairy Tail's
mightiest female wizard
will take on the
Scarlet Despair!
Next Time: "Master Enchant."
The power of love and
the bonds of friendship
will drive out this anguish.