[MAVIS screams]
[JACOB]
Hey!
Are you just refusing
to talk to me, or what?
I think I know who you are.
You're who the Emperor
was talking about.
The one he called Fairy Heart.
[MAVIS whimpering]
My guess is your body is
somewhere around here.
[MAVIS groans]
Talk.
[gasps, screams]
Regulus...
Fire Dragon...
--[LUCY] ...Lucy Kick!
--[NATSU] ...Talon!
[JACOB groaning]
You brats.
You've made this
grown-up very angry!
[INVEL] Now, we shall recommence
our advance on Fairy Tail.
Be on guard.
As our lone attacker made
perfectly clear earlier,
they're as reckless
as they are powerful.
Five of the elite Spriggan
Twelve have already fallen.
[SOLDIER A]
What?!
[SOLDIER B]
That's almost half!
[SOLDIER C]
I can't believe it!
[ZEREF]
Credit for the braggart's defeat
goes to Acnologia.
Be cautious, but unafraid!
For death itself could never
dare claim our leader!
Our victory is inevitable!
Forward, children of Alvarez!
We will deliver unto His
Majesty the Fairy Heart!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[ZEREF] I'm no longer
mired in hesitation.
Natsu. Mavis.
I shall extinguish your
lights once and for all.
[JACOB]
Huh?
[LUCY yells, gasps]
[NATSU gasps]
--[JACOB grunts]
--[NATSU groans]
He also knows martial arts?
[sighs]
Nice moves.
I'm not done.
[NATSU gasps, groans]
Huh? What--
[gasps, groans]
[BOTH groaning]
Hey! No fair!
Where is he? [groans]
Come on! Show your face!
You punks!
There's more pain in
the world than you know.
[BOTH groan]
I got 113 of your
mates tucked away
in a spot I made for 'em.
And I think it's about
time they started dying.
No, stop!
Don't hurt them, please!
[JACOB]
We've clearly crossed the line
where violence is
the only option.
[gasps]
Wait. Your friends!
What?
[LUCY] You've accidentally sent
one of your own away with them!
Brandish was here, too!
Was she?
[JACOB]
Hm? Brandish!
And that bloody wanker?
Damn it!
If I took her out with 'em,
Dimaria would never let
me hear the end of it.
[JACOB]
Right, then.
--[BRANDISH grunts]
--[MARIN sighs]
Stupid nobbers!
You're here now?
Thanks, man, that place
was so not chill!
Thanks, man! That place
was so not chill.
Uh?
[JACOB]
Uh--
[NATSU]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Wait, this dude is
stealing my look!
A-plus style!
Gemini!
Piri-piri!
--Whoa.
--It's creepy!
F-minus!
What?
It would've been a better
idea to turn into Brandish,
'cause that guy's way
weaker than her.
Actually, Gemini can't turn into
wizards as powerful as she is.
True, but I had another
reason for doing it this way.
Law of Space, activate!
Piri-Pikkiri!
[BOTH]
Uh--
But isn't this gonna
make Gemini disappear?
[LUCY] And I'll lose
this cute Star Dress.
But I'm okay with that.
My transporter! No!
[LUCY] This spell nullifies
all spatial magic.
You know what that means, right?
Oh, bollocks!
I can bring all my friends back.
Glad to be outta there!
We're saved!
Well done!
Need a hand, Lucy?
Yeah! Let's rock!
Damn.
Amazing! That was a
brilliant move, Lucy!
Way to go!
[JACOB]
Enough of this bloody nonsense!
Off to the pits of hell
with the lot of ya!
[JACOB]
Squishy?
Owie!
What the--?
[MAKAROV] You've got some real
nerve, hurting our First Master!
Today is when you show
"respect for the Aged," so...
...you should respect her
more than anyone else!
[JACOB groaning]
[MAVIS]
I've been around a while,
but technically I'm
still in my twenties!
[NATSU] Hey! Don't trash
our new guild hall!
[MAKAROV] I don't wanna
hear that from you!
[NATSU yelling]
[JACOB gasps]
[NATSU yells]
Well that's a nutty strategy.
Can't have Natsu trying to
fight at full strength inside.
Yeah, we just fixed this place.
Don't want the thing
to blow up already.
Whoa! He just made the
lake totally evaporate!
[ROMEO, MAX, WARREN]
That's crazy!
[NATSU]
Mode: Fire Dragon King!
[JACOB groaning]
Fire Dragon King...
--[JACOB yells]
--...Destruction Fist!
[JACOB gasps]
[ALL cheering]
[ALL laughing]
[JACOB groaning]
[chuckles]
[HAPPY]
Yay!
[HAPPY laughs]
[NATSU] Hey, Bran--uhh...
Brand-new-dress?
[HAPPY, LUCY]
It's Brandish!
They told me I wouldn't be
alive if it wasn't for you!
Thanks so much!
Yeah, thanks so much!
You really didn't have
to go back to the cell.
We weren't gonna keep you locked
up after all you've done for us!
[BRANDISH] I can't believe
you actually beat Jacob.
Makes sense now--
why Emperor Spriggan
told us that we shouldn't
underestimate you as an enemy.
[chuckles]
[BRANDISH]
But now you're out of luck...
Hm?
...because August is coming.
What's that mean?
Like, the month?
It's already September.
[BRANDISH] Back in Alakitasia,
August is a fearsome month--
one that brings
disaster and misfortune.
So everybody prays,
puts on their best behavior,
and tries to maintain
whatever righteous lifestyle
gets them through it.
August always brings
some kind of reckoning.
It's been thought of that
way for generations.
[clanking]
[WIZARD A] Hey! You mind
handing me that board?
[WIZARD B] We should let
Laki use her Wood Make Magic
to fix it quick!
[WIZARD C] No more
wrecking the place, Master!
[WIZARD D]
Seriously, act your age!
I apologize.
So what's the situation
out there, Warren?
Don't really know.
I think my radar is on
the fritz or something.
I hope it's not my fault.
No, doesn't seem
like it's damaged.
It's more like
someone out there is
purposefully jamming the signal.
That Jacob guy said his teammate
could mess with trackers.
I think he mentioned the
wizard's name was August, maybe?
You see, we have this
crafty old wizard
named August in our ranks.
He realized that our
movements were being watched,
so he had to go and
fix that, now didn't he?
That means August
is headed this way.
The man The Twelve call
"the Wizard King."
And he's coming here?
[MAX] So how do we send him
packin', First Master? Or, uh...
Is she just invisible,
or is she gone?
[ROMEO] I thought I
heard her say she was
going to the basement to heal.
[MAX]
Huh.
[WARREN]
Not so sure I understand
how a projection
can get hurt, but...
[MAX]
I dunno.
Wild.
I had no idea we
even had a basement.
It's been one of the guild's
biggest secrets for a while.
Because inside that
lacrima is my real body--
the everlasting magic,
Fairy Heart.
Which is what Zeref is after.
Yes.
[MAVIS]
Seeing the way Natsu and Lucy
fought against Jacob
earlier gave me an idea.
And I'm almost positive I know
how we can defeat Zeref.
[CANA]
Huh?
I can't go into much detail,
but it's absolutely crucial
that we free my real body
from that lacrima.
[CANA]
Hold on a second.
I mean, you're in
there, but, uh--
[MAVIS]
My body is theoretically alive,
which is likely thanks to
Precht's revival spells.
[CANA]
How do we get you out?
[MAVIS]
Fairy Glitter.
[CANA gasps]
You must use Fairy Glitter
to destroy my projection--
to eliminate this fake body.
[CANA gasps]
[MAVIS]
You see there?
When my projection was damaged
earlier, that crack appeared.
If my theory is correct,
eradicating my projection should
destroy the lacrima and free me.
What? Are you
serious about this?
You really want me
to attack you?
[MAVIS]
This is just an illusion.
You won't hurt me--in fact,
it's the opposite.
[CANA]
I can't! No!
It's way too risky!
If something were to happen
to the real you, I--
[MAVIS]
Cana.
You have to trust me.
This is the only way.
Don't forget our goal
is to beat Zeref.
[CANA gasps]
[PANTHERLILY]
There they are.
That's the enemy battalion.
We're pretty late for
our rendezvous
with Sabertooth
and Blue Pegasus.
I hope they're all right.
[LEVY]
They're coming this way!
What should we do?
[GAJEEL]
Whaddaya think? We fight 'em.
[LEVY] I dunno. Can we
take on that many?
[PANTHERLILY]
Don't worry.
The other guilds
should be close by.
If we gotta do it
alone, so be it.
These clowns ain't
marchin' on our guild.
Everyone better get
ready to fight!
[GAJEEL gasps]
[LEVY]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
Yukino.
That's Sting and Rogue!
Horrible!
[GAJEEL]
That is so messed up!
They're showin' 'em off.
[ERZA]
What's happening?
[KAGURA]
It's so dark.
[JELLAL]
Can't see a thing.
I know this magic.
[JELLAL groans]
[ERZA]
Jellal!
[ERZA groans]
[KAGURA groans]
[SIMON] Been awhile since
the gang was together.
Remember my Dark Moment spell?
Nostalgic, isn't it?
[ALL gasp]
[ERZA]
Simon...?
You're still... alive?
[SIMON] Erza. I'm glad
to see you're doing well.
And you seem very different
these days, Jellal.
And you... Could you be...?
Big brother.
[JELLAL grunts]
It's me!
[JELLAL]
Stay back!
[ERZA gasps]
This thing isn't Simon.
Bastard! How dare you?
[NEINHART chuckles]
[KAGURA, JELLAL, ERZA gasp]
[ERZA]
Huh?
[NEINHART] Your Historia
has a bit of everything--
love, pain, friendship,
heartbreak, death.
Oh, yes. You share a compelling
and beautiful Historia.
[KAGURA]
What does that mean?
[JELLAL] You must be one
of the Twelve shields.
[NEINHART grunts]
[ERZA]
This is your doing?
[NEINHART] I'm impressed
you grasped the situation
so quickly.
This is the manifestation
of your Historia--
a wizard you all
hold in your hearts.
[NEINHART] I can see
inside them, you know.
Your hearts are brimming
with memories and emotions.
I gather all those feelings
and give them physical form.
I am a creator of life--
my magnificent Historias.
[SIMON]
I can't believe it.
It's really you.
Kagura...
Big brother! [gasps]
[SIMON]
You've grown so... stro--
[KAGURA gasps]
[ERZA gasps]
[growls, grunts]
Control yourself!
It wasn't really him,
just an illusion!
[KAGURA]
Move aside!
[NEINHART] "Illusion"
is a bit of a misnomer.
You saw it yourselves.
I create lifeforms that can use
magic, among other things.
Living beings with
memories and feelings.
--[JELLAL grunts]
--[KAGURA gasps]
Take cover, now!
[ERZA gasps]
Jellal! Kagura!
[NEINHART chuckles]
[gasps]
You're here, too.
You thought our paths
would never cross again.
How wrong you were.
Trinity Raven's gone.
I saw you die!
[IKARUGA]
You merely released my soul.
[NEINHART] Ikaruga,
an exquisitely dangerous flower.
[KAGURA]
I can't die here with you!
Erza needs my help, immediately!
[KAGURA]
He's a murderer.
He killed my brother!
[ERZA grunting]
[ERZA groans, gasps]
You're not the warrior
I remember from years ago.
Perhaps the creep of time
has dulled your edge?
[ERZA gasps]
It must be her wounds.
The Erza I fought was
powerful and fierce.
Azuma!
Let's see.
Have you lost your strength?
Or are you just hiding it?
[ERZA grunts, gasps]
[ERZA gasps]
Bleve!
[ERZA screams]
[ERZA gasps]
[AZUMA grunts]
[ERZA yells]
Remember my Ramus Sica?
[IKARUGA]
Mugetsu Style.
Yasha-senku!
The more adversaries
a person has overcome,
the more splendid
their Historias.
This is my magic,
the Historia of Corpses.
With it, I can breathe new
life into battles of old.
Kyoka!
I see. So you've died, too?
Hush, Azuma.
I shan't discuss it.
[NEINHART]
These souls, that never had
the pleasure of
meeting before,
now interact as old friends.
Ahh, it's such a
marvelous thing.
Now, spread forth,
Historia of Corpses!
[KEYES]
Have the dead been revived?
Not quite.
This is not the same
as necromancer magic
that simply controls the dead.
[KEYES chuckles]
[KEYES]
How fascinating.
One's memories of powerful foes
they've faced are manifested,
returning for yet
another battle.
[ERZA yells, groans]
[IKARUGA] Surely you still
have the power to stand, Erza.
Get up. I wish to taste
your strength once more.
[NEINHART] Yes. What a
beautiful moment of creation.
Your hearts were
the fertile soil
from which my Historias
have sprung!
[KAGURA panting]
[sighs]
[ERZA yells]
[KAGURA]
Live!
[LUCY] Neinhart's Historias
enter the battlefield,
causing both physical
and emotional chaos.
Past adversaries emerge
one after another,
dragging everyone into
mortal confrontation.
Struggling against
three Historias,
Erza finds herself immobilized,
haunted by her memories
and wrapped within a prison
of her past pain and suffering.
Next time: "Mettle."
To overcome the past,
one must have the will
to live in the present.