[NATSU] Uh, so, is this just
some big stack of rocks?
[HAPPY] Uh, they're
called ruins, genius.
[NATSU and HAPPY yell]
[LOKE yells]
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU] Let's get
one thing straight.
There's no way I'm going to let
you guys forget about Lucy.
I just couldn't stand to see her
go through that kind of pain.
[LOKE] Hmph.
[NATSU grunts]
[LOKE chuckles]
That light of yours.
It looks darker now,
like it got dirty.
Why?
[LOKE] My light
is far from soiled.
It's just as pure as
my desire for freedom
and every bit as powerful!
Ha. There's one way
you haven't changed.
You're still full of crap!
[LOKE laughs]
The heck are
you laughing at?
[NATSU yells]
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
Pitch-Black Hammer!
Ah!
[HAPPY screams]
--[LOKE grunts]
--[HAPPY screams]
Happy! No!
[HAPPY yells]
[NATSU] Ah! Son of a...
[HAPPY whimpers]
[NATSU]
You okay, buddy?
You gotta hang in there!
I-I hid a fish in
your pillow, Natsu.
Give it to Carla for me.
[NATSU]
Good job, scumbag!
Thought you looked dirty,
now I know for sure!
Get down here and take
what you got coming!
[LOKE laughs]
[NATSU gasps]
[NATSU] What did I eat today?
Your flame burns
low, Dragneel.
[NATSU grunts]
[NATSU] C'mon...
You'll get no mercy.
Pitch-Black Punishment!
[NATSU retches]
[LOKE &amp; NATSU gasp]
[BOTH yell]
[HAPPY]
Wendy vs. Aquarius.
Let's Have Fun in
the Amusement Park!
[HISUI gasps]
I can't help but feel
that I should be there.
[LUCY] Let's end this.
--[LUCY grunts]
--[VIRGO giggles]
[LUCY shouts]
[VIRGO laughs]
[LUCY pants]
[VIRGO giggles]
You seem tired.
That makes it my turn.
"Let's end this!" That's what
you came for, right?
[LUCY grunts]
Feed me with your pain!
Every whimper charges my whip!
[LUCY] Please stop...
Beg away, but there's
no safety word with me!
That would ruin the fun!
[VIRGO laughs]
Down girl!
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY screams]
[VIRGO giggles]
[CANA growls]
[SCORPIO]
Shall I explain who I mean
when I tell you
that "I am the rules"?
Me, myself, not you.
[CANA]
That really isn't helpful!
You must be
eager to begin.
Enter standby sequence.
I deploy two Field Cards!
Face down!
[CANA] Don't think I
have those. Go fish!
Well, guess I'll have to
work it out by watching him.
Now for the fun part.
Enter battle sequence!
I summon spirits!
[CANA growls]
Piri, piri!
My name is Gemi!
And I'm Mini!
Are you going easy on me,
or is this just a warm-up?
Quite precisely
the opposite.
If you're as skilled
as I've heard,
then holding back
would be more than rude.
It would also be
a grievous mistake.
I'll press my advantage.
[CANA gasps]
[SCORPIO]
The unification of the Gemini
allows for a linked attack.
Together, they can destroy
any enemy monster
with less than five thousand
offensive points.
I said go fish!
I don't have any monsters so
you can't destroy them yet!
[CANA gasps]
You do lack monsters.
Which allows my Gemini
to attack you-- directly!
Piri, piri, pikkiri!
[CANA gasps]
[AQUARIUS] Pretty awesome
Amusement park, right?
And now that you're here,
I've got someone to play with!
No way!
I'm on a mission.
I don't have time
for dumb games!
My goodness child,
where did that come from?
You can say no without
that bullying tone.
[WENDY]
Hmph. I meant every word.
Boo on you.
Guess you like to be boring.
[AQUARIUS sighs]
But you won't spoil my fun.
I mean who cares if
you don't want to play?
If I use this,
you won't have a choice!
No way.
You should've been nice!
Ready or not!
Time to have fun!
[CARLA &amp; WENDY gasp]
[AQUARIUS] Ha, ha, ha!
See what I mean?
You've got to play
whatever I want now!
Just look, I've got an
awesome water twister!
[CARLA gasps]
[WENDY] Wow,
that's amazing.
Nice try, but it's too late
for sweet talk. Let's go!
Come on! She thinks
it's cool. Why don't you?
Aw... Hey, wait!
You haven't even seen
what it can do yet!
[WENDY] Stop it!
[CARLA] Wendy!
[AQUARIUS laughs]
[WENDY]
This isn't funny!
Stop! I don't think you want to
hurt us, but you're going to!
[WENDY gasps]
[CARLA] She may look like a
child, but her power's grown.
She's almost as
destructive as Natsu.
[AQUARIUS]
Uh oh!
It doesn't really look like
we're going to be able
to ride the horsies anymore.
Sorry about that.
[WENDY]
You could've hurt us!
[AQUARIUS] C'mon,
I want to keep on playing!
[WENDY] Look you, that is
not how playing works!
There's nothing fun
about getting attacked!
And if you can't
understand that,
then I'm going to
have to show you!
Sky Dragon Roar!
[CARLA &amp; WENDY scream]
[AQUARIUS]
That's the spirit you two.
I knew you'd come around!
--[CARLA whimpers]
--That could've gone better.
Do you feel well
enough to move?
Ugh. I'll try,
but no promises.
As soon as I can stand,
I'm going to give that
brat the what for!
Meanie!
That's what you are:
an evil, cackling, meanie!
Ah, "Meanie."
Such an eloquent word.
No I'm not,
I'm just playing!
Stop being such a sore loser!
You're a meanie!
No I'm not!
You are!
And a jerkface!
--It takes one to know one!
--Smart-Alec!
[CARLA] At least we aren't being
hunted by a water twister...
I suppose that this beats that.
[AQUARIUS]
You called me a meanie!
You shot me!
You kind of shot yourself.
Because of you!
Going to cry about it?
Of course not!
No... If I could pick,
I think I'd take the twister.
[WENDY] I'd rather eat my foot!
Look, it's going to make
me all kinds of mad
if you won't play
with me, you got it?
I'm serious!
I'm sorry, I don't speak meanie,
could you translate that?
[AQUARIUS]
You're making me mad!
Well I don't care!
You'd better stop
calling me a meanie!
'Cause you're the mean one!
[WENDY yells]
[CARLA]
So much for diplomacy.
Whoa, you're fast!
Hey, let's play tag instead!
[WATER MONSTER roars]
[WENDY screams]
[WENDY] Dad gummit, this is
nothing like tag!
I'm tired of running,
let me at her!
This little brat needs
to be taught a lesson!
Take me to the ground, Carla!
[CARLA] That's far
too dangerous!
You've seen how powerful she is!
Come on!
Look, Carla!
I can do this!
[AQUARIUS laughs]
[WATER MONSTER 209A]
Beat those tiny wings
as fast as you can!
[WATER MONSTER roars]
[WENDY &amp; CARLA scream]
Aw, the poor
guy bit himself...
But I think he's
going to be okay.
[WATER MONSTER roars]
Oh. Guess they're hiding, huh?
Yay!
You know what that means:
Hide-and-go-seek!
That's our most
favorite game ever!
[WATER MONSTER roars]
No clues?
They're good hiders!
Fine. We'll have
to flush them out!
[WATER MONSTER roars]
[WENDY gasps]
This girl's crazy!
What do we do?!
[WENDY &amp; CARLA gasp]
So that's where
you were hiding!
I'm going to get you now!
Ow, What's the deal
with these raindrops?!
They're as sharp as knives!
Aw. I could've sworn
I'd get them with that one!
Uh, excuse me, Aquarius?
[CARLA] Be more assertive!
What gives you
the right to do this?
The entire amusement park
is in shambles 'cause of you!
Now there's lots of
broke stuff to hide in!
[WENDY] Nu-uh!
No more Hide-and-Seek!
Fine! There are tons
and tons more games
that we can play
around here!
You are really
difficult to talk to!
What you did was dangerous,
and you need to realize that!
[CARLA] Sheesh.
If you'd asked me to
drop you, I would've.
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon...
...Wing Attack!
Wait a second,
time-out!
Say what?
I spy someplace tasty,
right over that way.
[WENDY] Huh?
You do? What is it?
I'm pointing
right at it, silly!
Uh... yeah.
Could I have another clue?
It's two against one.
Why not fight me?
What do you think
of my swimming, Ma?
I've been practicing
my freestyle!
[PISCES MOM] You swim
beautifully, snookums.
[PISCES BOY] Cut it out
with the pet names!
Forget you, Hag, I can
take her out all by myself!
[PISCES MOM]
Why do you hate me so?
You've called
me mean names
and you've fought
girls without me,
but both at once?
I can barely take it!
I won't hurt you!
[MIRAJANE growls]
I spy someplace tasty,
right over that way!
[WENDY] Huh?
You do? What is it?
I'm pointing
right at it, silly!
Uh. Yeah.
Could I have another clue?
The ice cream shop,
doofus, let's go!
Uh, you...
want ice cream?
Okay, but this isn't exactly
the best time for treats.
[AQUARIUS giggles]
Let's go! I'm sure
you'll like it!
[AQUARIUS giggles]
Oh, look, diplomacy
has resumed.
[AQUARIUS] I hope
you're as excited as I am!
Cause you're in for
a crazy good treat!
Hurry up, Wendy,
you walk like an old lady!
[AQUARIUS giggles]
I'm all for talking this out.
But there's a key
difference between
speaking to your foe and letting
her lead you into a trap!
Ice cream...
No! Don't be a fool!
She'll give you worse
than a brain freeze!
[AQUARIUS]
Here you go!
Thank you!
Wow, it looks delicious!
[AQUARIUS]
You're welcome!
Nothing like some
break-time ice cream!
More like death cream.
Don't eat that.
I have reason to believe
that it's been poisoned.
There's no telling
what she might've--
[AQUARIUS]
Hey, kitty?
I made this one for you!
[CARLA] Oh.
Thank you.
Wait, I can't accept
this, take it back!
Then give it to me.
What? You actually
ate some of it?
I told you this was
awesome ice cream!
I give in.
Well, it doesn't particularly
taste like it's been poisoned.
[AQUARIUS] I've tasted
every flavor of ice cream here!
And you know what?
I still can't pick a favorite!
[WENDY] It's a big decision.
Don't rush yourself.
[CARLA] This stuff is more
than not bad. It's... decent.
[WENDY] I have a scoop
of ice cream with you
and now it feels
like we're friends.
[AQUARIUS]
We are.
Plus it was two scoops,
so we're double friends.
[AQUARIUS hums]
[WENDY giggles]
[AQUARIUS giggles]
Hey! Eyes off my chocolate.
[WENDY giggles]
Touch your nose.
[AQUARIUS laughs]
[WENDY giggles]
[CARLA] My!
This is more than decent.
So, was it as
yummy as promised?
It was the best dessert
I've ever had.
[giggling]
Now that we're friends,
we should stop fighting.
[AQUARIUS]
What're you talking about?
We never fought.
[WENDY] Huh?
We were playing,
remember?
So let's get back to it!
But, I don't like that game.
And we just had ice cream,
two scoops each,
that means we're friends!
Put down the urn!
Please don't hurt me!
[CARLA] Wait, I haven't
finished mine.
I said it was a trap,
but did you listen? No!
You really are
a quick one!
[WENDY &amp; CARLA scream]
What was that?!
[WENDY grunts]
[WENDY screams]
This isn't good!
We're sitting ducks
up here, Carla!
Hey, what happened?
Are you okay?
Just peachy,
why do you ask?
Because your spirit friend
shot me with her magic urn?
Or because the only limbs
that I can move
are my stubby
little legs? Help me!
I'll try, but I don't know
if I can reach that far.
[CARLA] You can't just
tug on my foot!
You'll have to pull
me from the inside!
[WENDY grunts]
[WENDY] Okay, got it.
So, I don't think
I can get in there.
[CARLA] What do
you mean by that?!
She's coming!
[CARLA] Do something, quickly!
Wow, such a pretty view
and I'm only halfway up!
Bet yours is even better!
Enjoy it while you can!
Please stop shooting!
You'll knock down
the whole Ferris Wheel!
Ha, ha, ha!
Sounds like fun!
I think I'll aim for
something fragile this time!
Like me?!
Awww...
[WENDY gasps
[NATSU screaming]
[WENDY] Whoa, is that Natsu?
Sounds like him!
[NATSU] Look out below!
That's weird.
Didn't think that
meteors could yell.
[NATSU &amp; HAPPY scream]
[NATSU groans]
[NATSU] Don't worry, Wendy...
Natsu to the rescue...
[WENDY] You two look
horrible, what happened?
Are you all right?
[HAPPY] There's not a fur on
my body that feels all right.
Loke blew us straight
out of his world
with this crazy-strong attack.
[NATSU] Yup.
Is it just me or is that
happening way too much lately?
[CARLA] Happy! Happy!
Look over here!
Uhh... Carla!
I sure am glad that you're okay!
Do I seem okay?!
My head's stuck
in a pane of glass.
Get over here and
pull me out, please!
[HAPPY]
No problem!
[BOTH grunt]
Try to be gentle!
[CARLA] That was way more rough!
--Sorry.
--Hurry!
[BOTH grunt]
[HAPPY] Hey look,
I'm trying my best here,
but the thing is that.
I just took a pretty
serious beat-down,
so I'm feeling kind of woozy.
Tell it to me straight, Wendy.
Does this thing move?
It's supposed to,
but not right now.
Well, that's a relief.
[AQUARIUS] If you've
got Natsu up there,
tell him that he
hasta play with us!
Why does she know
who I am, anyway?
She's gotten way smaller, huh?
Is she less scary now?
[WENDY and NATSU yell]
[AQUARIUS laughs]
[NATSU] Hey! Watch
where you're aiming!
[WENDY] Ah!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon
Brilliant Flame!
[ferris wheel groans]
Listen to that, it sounds
like the Ferris wheel's
about to fall apart!
Well, is there something
we can do to stop it?
To be honest,
I think our best shot is to jump
off of it while we still can!
You can't be serious.
[CARLA] Happy! Take Wendy
and Natsu to the ground
for me, okay?
No way, I am not going
to leave you behind!
Also, I'm still weak from
that fight with Loke.
I can barely even keep
myself in the air.
Sheesh, you're even more
useless than usual.
[HAPPY] Aww...
Check it out!
It's shaking!
All right, guess we'll
have to wing it!
You ready for this?
[WENDY gasps
[NATSU yells]
[CARLA grunts]
[CARLA gasps]
You did it!
Piece of cake!
[AQUARIUS laughs]
Excuse me, Aquarius?
[CARLA] Now you're
being too nice.
This place isn't safe anymore,
so we're going to leave.
I think that you
should come with us!
Stop being such
a spoilsport.
I want to keep on playing!
This thing's on its
last leg, Aquarius.
Get the heck away
before it crushes you!
[NATSU yells]
You're right, it is
going to fall down!
Isn't that exciting?
Guess we're doing
this the hard way!
Fire Dragon Roar!
Water puts out fire,
stupid. So you lose.
[NATSU growls]
[AQUARIUS groans]
Way to go!
[NATSU laughs]
--[WENDY sighs]
--[CARLA] He did it!
[AQUARIUS whimpers]
No fair...
I'm only a little girl,
you're supposed to let me win.
Meanie!
[AQUARIUS wails]
The heck, man?
What's she crying about?
From what I heard,
you're a meanie.
I'm nice and you know it!
[wailing continues]
You know what, Aquarius?
From the things Lucy
told me about you,
I thought that you'd
be really scary.
But you're not at all!
[CARLA &amp; WENDY gasp]
[NATSU whimpers]
[HAPPY screams]
[AQUARIUS gasps]
[WENDY gasps]
We have to break her fall!
But I'm not done
playing yet!
[AQUARIUS screams]
[WENDY and CARLA yell]
[NATSU] Hey, Don't go!
[HAPPY] Carla!
[NATSU] Hey... don't go...
[WENDY] Aquarius, I'm coming!
There's only one way.
Sky Dragon Roar!
[AQUARIUS] Whoa!
That was fun, right?
[AQUARIUS giggles]
[HAPPY growls]
--[HAPPY giggles]
--You saved me!
[HAPPY] Of course!
I won't ever let you fall!
[NATSU screams]
Hey, didn't you just tell us
you were too beat-up to fly?!
You got to fight through the
pain to save the ones you love.
[HAPPY] You gotta fight
through the pain
to save the ones you love...
Yes, I suppose that's true...
[NATSU] You couldn't
get me after?! Aaahh!
[crashing sound]
[NATSU]
I... I don't believe it...
How could you forget me...?
Good job!
Thanks again for saving me!
That would've hurt!
Oh no, you're
all dirty now.
Like I care, I just want
to go out and have fun!
Let's do this again, just with
less danger and more ice cream.
Okay, but can my games
really be that dangerous?
Yeah, they're
extremely dangerous.
And not just for
the people around you,
you nearly hurt yourself bad.
Yeah. I'll try to be careful.
We will play again
someday, won't we?
But maybe we should
play cards instead.
[AQUARIUS giggles]
I had fun, thanks!
You're welcome.
Thank you!
[NATSU groans]
Well look at that:
they made up again.
You've been here for a long time
now, do you want to go home?
Yeah. Think I'm ready.
Remember, we're
double scoop friends.
How could I forget?
I'll see you later, Wendy.
[WENDY sighs]
[CARLA] Well, that's one
mission accomplished.
Now if someone would stop
slacking off in his crater,
we could get moving.
Don't start with me,
you dirty traitor!
[HAPPY]
Standby Sequence!
I play twenty field cards!
[NATSU] Uh, what're you
going on about, man?
[HAPPY]
Don't you know?
There's a whole new
battle card game!
It's a craze!
[NATSU] Huh.
Sounds cool to me.
What're the rules?
[HAPPY] Don't be
ridiculous, man!
It's a battle card game.
Why would there be rules?
[NATSU]
So you know how to play?
[HAPPY] If you let a rulebook
tell you how to play,
then you'll never
develop your own style.
Oh! It's my turn!
[NATSU and HAPPY] Next Time:
Guild Deck vs. Celestial Deck.
[HAPPY] Guild Battle Standby!
[NATSU] Okay, but seriously.
How do you play?