[NATSU, HAPPY]
Ooh!
[LUCY]
Cool!
[HAPPY]
They look so pretty!
[NATSU] Yeah They look nice,
but where'd they come from?
They're gifts from
a satisfied customer!
We took a little
job from this old guy
who's obsessed with pool.
When we stopped at
his place to get paid,
he showed us the basics and
we all played a few rounds.
[GRAY] And as it just so
happens, I'm a natural.
[LUCY] I guess you can
take all kinds of payment
when your landlady
isn't stalking you.
[JUVIA] Well, he paid us,
this was more of a bonus.
[GRAY] We had such a good
time playing at his place
he gave us these so the
whole guild could try!
Seriously, what a nice guy!
Aye!
Right then, check this out!
[JUVIA gasps]
Uh. Do you have to play naked?
If you wanna be a pro.
You strip in public
professionally, now, do ya?
Shut up so I can focus.
I'll let you in on a secret.
If you want to rock it at
pool, you have to become
one with your magic first.
What'll it take for you to
become one with me, darling?
Huh, he does look
pretty cool right now.
Back off wench, he's mine!
Kay. Just watch and learn.
[NATSU, HAPPY]
Ooh!
[GRAY] You know what
my favorite sound is?
The clack of a ball
in the pocket.
If it's your favorite
sound then it must
be mine as well, darling!
[HAPPY]
It really is like magic, huh?
[MALE 203A] Whoa!
[MALE 203B] How's he do it?
[MALE 203C]
Crazy!
[GRAY]
Just wait till you see this.
That's amazing Gray,
you're so talented.
For once he has me impressed.
I'd expect nothing less
from the love of my life!
It's bouncing.
And it's in.
Now for the finale.
And that is how you
play a game of pool.
[CROWD gasps]
That was incredible!
He certainly did
put on a show.
Oh, Do you think that you could
do it for us one more time?
Pretty smooth, Gray.
I never would've guessed
you had it in you.
If you want to learn
how to play sometime,
I can show ya a trick or two.
Twice I've warned you now.
[LUCY gasps]
Okay! Let me take
a crack at this game.
[WENDY] Um, that's not
exactly how you're supposed
to hold the cue.
[CARLA] The way he
holds it is about to be
the least of our worries.
Something tells me you've
never played this game before.
Nah. But I'm gonna be
a natural, I can feel it!
Just try not to hurt anybody.
Alright kid,
there's just one rule!
You gotta put the balls
in the holes, understand?
[NATSU] I already knew that,
so shut up and pitch,
but don't throw
me any curveballs.
[LUCY] They could be joking.
Yeah, maybe that's it.
I don't know what
those two are playing,
but if they're having a
good time, then who cares?
You're so mature and confident.
I knew you'd be the bigger man.
[CARLA] I'm beginning
to think that we should
take a few steps back.
Par five, first down.
This is your moment, rookie!
Fore!
[CROWD screaming]
[LUCY screams]
Eight down, two outs,
bases loaded!
[NATSU yells]
[FAIRY TAIL]
Didn't I tell you not
to hurt anybody?
Yeah, I should've
seen this coming.
Don't worry Gray! If they
break all the pool balls,
then you can play
with me instead!
Give it a rest!
[HAPPY] Looks like a hole
in none strike out.
Hit it like you
mean it next time!
[NATSU]
That's great advice!
When at first you don't
succeed, hit stuff harder!
[LUCY] Put that down
before you kill someone!
Who's making such a racket?
I could hear you from upstairs.
[NATSU]
I got it this time!
[ALL gasp]
Sorry about that,
nice catch though.
A cue ball, eh?
We were just breaking
in these pool tables.
Do you wanna join
us for a round?
With the balls on the floor?
Have you ever played?
Yes.
[ERZA] Many years ago,
I played it well.
[NATSU]
Huh?
[HAPPY]
Moulin Rouge
[MAN 203A]
Check it out.
You use your cue to
hit this white ball into
the numbered balls
and knock 'em
into those pockets, got it?
You sink the balls in order,
and whoever bags
that 9-ball, wins.
Takes a lot of focus, girlie,
might not be your game.
[MALE CROWD cackling]
[ERZA]
Thanks for the advice.
I think I grasp the rules.
Shall we begin?
Look, knowing the
rules doesn't make
ya a player, sweetheart.
Now Requip!
That's transformation magic!
What's a wizard doing
in our pool hall?
[ERZA]
Erza Scarlet. Bunny mode.
[MAN 203B]
You can hang here, anytime!
[MAN 203C]
What he said!
[ERZA]
The snow white orb.
Evocative of a maiden
pure as she is brave.
What the hell is this
chick talkin' about?
Cornered by the motley
servants of evil.
She smites them all!
[MALE CROWD gasping]
She just shattered
every single ball!
Poor things didn't
stand a chance.
Don't hurt us, lady!
Your balls were weak.
The tail of this
bunny suit is stronger.
I destroyed seven of
the nine with ease.
You don't understand
the rules at all!
This chick is trouble, man,
just tell her that she won!
[ERZA] With my next attack,
I'll turn the last two balls
into tiny mounds of dust.
[MAN 203C]
Uh, could ya not?
[MAN 203D] Puttin' the
whole freakishly strong
bunny-wizard thing aside:
if you don't play pool,
why are you here?
I'm glad you asked
that question.
What with all this ball-busting,
I almost forgot what I came for.
Please don't say "ball-busting."
I've heard tell far and
wide of your delicious
caramel mousse and
decided I must have it.
[MAN 203J]
You want some caramel?
[MAN 203K]
There's no mousse here.
[MAN 203L]
We don't got any.
[ERZA] A pack of
mousse hoarders, are we?
Fine, I know the
cure to your affliction.
And I have ways
of making you talk.
[MAN 203E]
There is a sweetshop next door!
[MAN 203D] Read the sign
in front next time!
It seems I was mistaken.
It's no big deal!
[MAN 203B]
Ditzy or not,
you're still the
toughest girl I've seen.
You're already here, so why
not kick back for a while?
[MAN 203D]
Sorry, but you're in my way.
That emblem.
No!
[MAN 203E] She's with
Fairy Tail, run for your lives!
[ERZA]
Wait a second.
I am with Fairy Tail, but
there's no need to be afraid.
[MAN 203M] Stay back!
Don't hurt me, please!
[MAN 203N] Whatever it is, we're
sorry! We won't do it anymore!
[MAN 203O] Please let me go.
it's my daughter's birthday!
What is wrong with you?
Mercy! I've got five little
kids depending on me!
And a cat!
You tell your friend
Moulin Rouge,
we don't want any trouble.
[ERZA] Who's that?
I've never heard of her.
Stop pretending not
to know your own ally!
[ERZA] I have no cause
to deceive you, sir.
So please, tell me.
Just who is this Moulin Rouge?
A rampaging bandit's
what she is.
From what I hear, she's an
immigrant from across the sea.
[ERZA]
Interesting.
[MAN 203D] She's lightning
fast and lives for danger.
[MAN 203E]
She's a menace.
Has a partner named Sonny.
Nobody's seen him and lived.
[BARTENDER 203A]
Don't know why those no-good
foreigners came to our town.
Five days ago they rode
out and robbed a train.
But that wasn't near enough
to satisfy their greed.
'Cause they robbed a
bank the day after that!
Shot it up too!
She'll kill you,
quick as look at you!
I only feel safe in your arms!
Seems fishy. If she
was staging robberies
of that caliber, I would've
heard about at least one.
Well she says she
did it, and I've never
been one for asking
deadly bandits questions!
[MAN 203A] It's not that we're
too afraid to stand up to her.
Lots of people have tried!
But She beat the tar
out of every one of them.
I still have
nightmares about it.
Nobody around here is
strong enough to take her on.
[MAN 203E] Just the sound of her
name can make me pee my pants.
If you can't handle this
bandit problem by yourselves,
then why haven't you
contacted Fairy Tail about it?
What a terrible idea!
She's a member of
that beastly guild!
If any of her
friends got involved,
they could wipe our
town right off the map!
Wouldn't be the first time
either, they're known for it!
Give a city job to
Fairy Tail wizards,
and they'll leave it in ruins.
Even the Magic Council's
afraid of those jerks.
As they get bigger
and more powerful,
they'll only destroy
even more stuff!
A small percentage of that
felt vaguely accurate.
But before you
judge us look at me!
You don't think I'm
ferocious, do you?
Course not, I'm a bunny girl!
[MAN 203P]
Oh you're totally scary.
[MAN 203Q]
Just look at what you did!
[MAN 203R]
The balls you busted are gonna
burn through the table!
[MAN 203S]
The bunny suit makes it scarier.
[ERZA]
I apologize.
The point is, that thieving,
good for nothing,
cut-throat, immigrant is backed
by one of the biggest guilds
on the continent so there's
nothin' we can do to stop her!
Unforgivable.
[BARTENDER 203A screams]
Usurping the sacred
name of Fairy Tail
in order to prey upon the weak.
Now, wait, could you say that
last thing one more time?
Almost sounded like
you said Moulin Rouge
wasn't a Fairy Tail wizard!
You heard me.
[BARTENDER 203A screams]
[ERZA] Tell me, where can
I find this besmircher
of my guild's good name?
[MAN 203A] Well, earlier
she went into the sweetshop
next door. Might still be there.
[MAN 203B] If you're really are
from Fairy Tail, then good luck.
Teach her a lesson!
[ERZA]
Oh, I intend to.
Hi, welcome to Fruits Park.
That's a nice bunny suit.
[ERZA]
I'd love to buy some sweets,
but first there's someone
that I need to stalk.
[SERVER 203A]
Uh...
[ERZA]
What an adorable uniform!
I'll borrow this to
get closer to my mark.
[ERZA]
Meanwhile, this is for you.
It's the only one there is:
Gorgeous, I know.
At times like this I take
great pleasure in my work.
I'm not just cute.
I'm well disguised.
[SERVER 203A] I wish you'd
let me be the bunny girl.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
What is this crap?
It's so sweet it makes me sick!
But, um, it's exactly
what you ordered, Ma'am.
[MOULIN ROUGE] Did I order
butterfly crap dipped in sugar?
[SERVER 203B]
Well, no Ma'am.
You ordered an ice cream
and some tea, but--
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Oh, is that what I have here?
Yes, our ice cream
is served with--
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Butterfly crap!
I know what you put on
it so don't bother lying!
What, do you want me to get your
manager out here, is that it?
[SERVER 203B] I would,
but she isn't at work today.
I seek Moulin Rouge. Know her?
Yeah. You got her right here.
I'm seeking
Moulin Rouge. You know her?
Yeah. You got her right here.
[SERVER 203A]
Looks like the bunny girl wants
a piece of Moulin Rouge!
I think we should hide.
I'm trying to eat here, so tell
me what you want or get lost.
Rumor has it that you're
a Fairy Tail wizard.
Damn right I am.
What's it to you?
[ERZA] You plan to pay for
your dessert with a bogus
complaint and the threat of
Fairy Tail's wrath. Despicable.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
What?
Here's how it works: you piss me
off, you provoke my whole guild.
So back off.
I have friends who could
turn this crappy little town
of yours into a crater, got it?
[ERZA] Fairy Tail has
been provoked, indeed.
And we will make
you pay dearly.
[MOULIN ROUGE gasps]
You've been running your mouth
plenty lately, haven't you?
Since these will be
your last words,
you should make them count.
No way!
How did you get the
massive sword in here?
[FEMALE CUSTOMER 203A]
They're crazy!
[MALE CUSTOMER 203A]
Run while you still can!
[FEMALE SERVER 203A]
Did she seriously need to change
her clothes for that?
[LUCY] I didn't even get to
eat my caramel mousse.
This isn't fair!
[BARTENDER 203A] Sounds like
a stampede out there.
[MAN 203A]
Think it's bunny girl?
[MAN 203B] It's either
that or an earthquake.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Damn. Caught red-handed
by the genuine article.
How awkward is this?
[ERZA] So much for making
your last words count.
Look fairy-girl, they call
me the lightning bandit
here and I've got a theory why.
You might get
struck by lightning
but it's way too quick to catch!
[ERZA]
Such speed!
[MOULIN ROUGE cackles]
[ERZA screams]
[MALE CROWD gasping]
[MOULIN ROUGE]
These are such cute uniforms.
And so very
convenient to remove!
Give it back right now!
Pay my tab, will ya?
Coward.
[ERZA]
Before it wasn't personal.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Huh?
[ERZA] But disrobing me in
the very place where I should
be eating Caramel Mousse
right now has sealed your doom.
I think you have
some anger issues!
Wait, please!
[MOULIN ROUGE groans]
[CROWD screams]
What the heck was that?
[MAN 203B] That whole wall
exploded, that's what!
[MAN 203D] Sweet mother of--
It's that girl from before!
[MAN 203E]
Oh no. I think she's with--
[MAN 203F]
Moulin Rouge!
[MAN 203A]
Why would you bring her here?
Get ready.
That was just a warm up.
[BARTENDER 203A]
Can't you take it outside?
[MOULIN ROUGE]
I have to admit.
You're a bit tougher
than I took you for.
Watch yourself!
That foul migrant's a
master of the quick-draw!
[ERZA]
A master, are you? Intriguing.
Go ahead and draw.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Okay.
Whoa, look, I'm not one
to give tips to my enemies,
but fighting a gun with
a sword is suicide.
Even if I weren't the quickest
draw on the continent.
Still running that mouth?
Cease this bragging
and draw your weapon.
Fine then. We'll do it your way.
At least you won't say
I didn't warn ya.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Since you'll be dead!
[MALE CROWD screaming]
[MAN 203T]
Did I just see that?
[MAN 203U] What kind of
Samurai crap did she just pull?
I knew she was trouble,
but I didn't know how much!
No frickin' way was that real.
I must've missed or something!
Screw you!
[MALE CROWD yelping]
No way!
[MAN 203V]
You saw that, right?
[MAN 203W] She knocked
the one ball into a pocket.
[MAN 203X]
So she does know the rules!
[ERZA] I thought you
said you were fast.
Compared to what?
Those tiny cue balls
you just lobbed at me?
What are you,
some kind of monster?
Stand still!
[ERZA grunting]
[MOULIN ROUGE growling]
[MOULIN ROUGE growls]
[MOULIN ROUGE gasps]
[MALE CROWD]
Oh!
[ERZA]
Admit your defeat.
[MOULIN ROUGE whimpers]
You could try.
But as I've already
wrapped up my game of pool,
the only place I'll send
that bullet is back.
You wench!
I'm sorry, okay? I messed up.
Dang. Moulin Rouge just
admitted she was beaten!
The real Fairy Tail
girl is incredible!
Considering what
she pulled earlier,
I guess we shouldn't
be that surprised.
Glad that's settled.
[ERZA]
The punishment for misusing
Fairy Tail's name is severe.
I knew it was wrong,
but I'm a migrant.
[ERZA] What does that
have to do with it?
They don't trust
foreigners here.
I haven't been able
to find a single job.
And now you've all but
justified that prejudice.
Think of how they'll
treat the next immigrant.
Stealing is the only way
for me to make end's meet!
Look at me,
I'm obviously not rich.
I take enough to survive,
and that's it.
What little money I do get,
I put it towards Sonny's
medicine without it, he'd die!
You damn foreigner.
I was wrong about you!
Makes me think of my five kids.
What about your cat, man?
[MOULIN ROUGE]
I can't take back my crimes.
But I do promise that I
won't cause these people
any more trouble!
Please let me go.
If I died, so would Sonny,
and none of this is his fault!
[ERZA]
It's okay. I won't kill you.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
Thank you.
[MAN 203BB]
Ain't it beautiful?
[MAN 203CC]
Such a simple gesture of peace!
There are other
ways to take revenge!
[MALE CROWD screams]
[MOULIN ROUGE screams]
Given the circumstances,
I could turn a blind eye to
your banditry. But I will never
tolerate the deliberate
abuse of Fairy Tail's name.
You've brought shame
to my guild,
and that crime is
all but unforgivable!
Every single choice that
a Fairy Tail wizard makes
is a reflection of the values
upheld by the guild itself.
The symbol we bear
is no mere decoration.
It's the sigil of a family.
The emblem of our pride.
[MALE CROWD gasps]
[ERZA] When we're marked,
we take an oath:
forever binding our fates
to that of the guild.
And should anyone dare
trample upon that sacred oath:
good or wicked,
I will cut them down.
[MALE CROWD yelps]
Don't cut me, I'm already down!
I didn't know what I was doing
but I get it now. I'm sorry!
[MOULIN ROUGE shrieks]
[ERZA] That's what it
means to be in a guild.
Don't forget.
[MOULIN ROUGE]
But why?
If you're looking for
work, come to Fairy Tail.
I think you'd fit right in.
[MOULIN ROUGE] Hey, wait! My
real name isn't Moulin Rouge!
It's Bisca! Bisca Mulan!
[BISCA]
Um. I didn't catch yours.
It's Erza. Erza Scarlet.
I won't forget.
[BISCA]
She's the coolest! Right, Sonny?
[MALE CROWD] You robbed
us blind to save a mouse?
[BARTENDER 203A]
I hope Fairy Tail cares about
its reputation as
much as she does.
'Cause they're about to
get a huge repair bill.
[ALL]
How's it going?
Great! You wrap up
that job already?
Welcome home!
Come check this out real quick.
[ALZACK] Hey, these are
really nice tables, man.
where'd you get 'em?
Well see, it's kind
of a long story,
and I just finished tellin' it.
They're gifts from a client
that really likes pool.
I guess it's a shorter
story than I thought.
Pretty! What're you supposed
to do with this stuff?
Do you see those
numbers on the balls?
Yup, yup!
[HAPPY] Get a stick, then knock
'em in the holes countin' up!
[ASCA] Sounds tough, but I
bet you'd be good Happy!
[CARLA] Those aren't the
rules you went by earlier.
Hey Carla, would you like
to play a round with me?
[CARLA] Until I know
more about the game
than Happy, I'll refrain.
Well this takes me back.
Yes, that makes two of us.
[BOTH giggle]
[BISCA] You know, I've never
seen you play for real.
Ever tried?
[ERZA]
Once or twice.
[BISCA] Well, the last
time I saw you play,
your pool cue was a katana.
[ERZA]
Is that not how you play?
Guess I haven't after all.
[LUCY]
Hey! What cha talkin' about?
Not a whole lot.
We're just reminiscing about
how I met my family here.
Yes. I'm glad you found us.
[HAPPY] This bites,
it's been raining for days.
Geez guys, when do you
think it's going to stop?
[GRAY]
The hell it is!
Get your damp head away from me!
Not until you stop
dripping on my coat!
[ERZA] I'm sick of
this mindless feuding.
Play nice!
[NATSU]
But Gray started it this time!
[GRAY]
Are you lying or just stupid?
[NATSU, GRAY gasp]
[HAPPY]
There's someone at the door
[NATSU]
Who the heck is that?
[GRAY]
How would I know, man?
[ERZA] You came after all.
I've been waiting.
Hey, Erza. It's good to see you.
[BISCA]
I was wondering.
There anything around for a
girl and her partner to eat?
Yeah, of course. How's your
sickly friend been doing?
[SONNY squeaks]
[ERZA]
Oh, so this is Sonny.
His medicine's
expensive, I hear.
Yeah, it can be
hard to keep up with.
I'm penniless at the moment.
The Chef's name is Mira.
That stew is her
best dish, so dig in.
[BISCA]
Thank you.
Like it?
[BISCA]
It's really warm.
So you're a friend
of Erza's, huh?
Mira makes a pretty
tasty stew, am I right?
What is it? Is the food
not to your liking?
[BISCA] No, it's just,
I already owe you.
But could I have a job?
[ERZA]
Sure.
Hey, you should've
told us she's a wizard!
This changes everything!
I know we just met, but I'm
thinkin' we should fight!
There's no need for that.
I fought her myself.
[GRAY]
And she's walking?
[NATSU]
The girl's hardcore!
[BISCA]
Um. Thanks, but--
We'll get you one of these
once you're done eatin'!
This symbol we bear is no
mere decoration though, okay?
It's the sigil of a family.
[ERZA] Before that, you should
meet the guild-master.
[HAPPY]
C'mon, let's mark her up now!
[SONNY groans]
Up for a match?
[BISCA]
Just don't whip any swords out.
[ALZACK] Wait a minute.
I didn't know you played pool!
Just watch and learn, babe.
Closest lag shot breaks.
Square off, the game begins.
[WENDY] Wow! Both of them
look like they're pros!
[CARLA]
They do have excellent form!
[HAPPY] Put the balls
in the holes, alright?
[ASCA]
You're the coolest, Momma!
Let's do this.
All right.
[NATSU]
Lucy's wigging out, dude!
What's goin' on?
[HAPPY] Oh yeah, she wants
to throw some kind of
party for all those
celestial spirit people!
[NATSU]
A party?
[HAPPY] Yep. They had us
over to their place before
the Grand Magic Games, so it's
like the least that we could do.
[NATSU] Oh. Well when
you put it that way,
I guess we outta give
her a hand, right?
[HAPPY]
Well yeah.
But the thing is: I feel like
we're overdue for some trouble.
[NATSU, HAPPY] Next Time:
Full Effort Hospitality!
[NATSU] Hey!
What does this job have to do
with hosting a party?
[HAPPY] Ugh. I don't
know, man. I give up.