[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Unforgivable.
I'm afraid I might
enjoy killing you so much
my heart will explode with joy.
You need to show some
respect for your mother.
And since she's not around
I'll have to teach you
that lesson for her!!!
No, Ultear!
[ULTEAR]
Don't worry about me!
I want you to hurry and take
Zeref to the escape point!
[MELDY]
Right!
Hey Juvia!
Time to wake up!
It's my beloved Gray!
Ah, waking to the gentle
whispers of my love's voice.
I can't think of a better way
to start my morning.
[GRAY]
Snap out of it!
[HAPPY]
"Power of Life"!
[GRAY] You've gotta
go after her, Juvia!
Don't let her
get away with Zeref!
'Kay!
Ugggh!
My leg.
Are Yu hurt?
Yes, but I can handle it!
[JUVIA] I'll do
anything for my beloved.
A little pain isn't
going to stop me!
[GRAY]
I'm counting on you, Juvia.
Ice Make Lance!
I'll simply cast
your ice into its future!
[ULTEAR]
Sublimation!
[LUCY]
Arc of Time?
[HAPPY] Yeah, that's the kind of
Lost Magic she uses; apparently,
it can control time but
it doesn't have any effect
on living things.
In that case, I'm worried
about Gray 'cause
there's a good chance
he'll end up fighting her.
Will his Ice-Make
magic be enough?
I Dunno.
It'll be a tough fight;
she beat up Natsu without
even breakin' a sweat!
She didn't "beat me up."
Let's get one thing straight,
even if Gray does run into that
cross-dressin' geezer, there
ain't no way I'm gonna help him.
He'll have to
handle it on his own.
Don't be a jerk!
All I'm sayin' is I know
the guy, and he'll wanna
kick her butt by himself
without a buncha people getting
in the way.
[HAPPY] You guys have known
each other a long time and
it's pretty obvious you two
share a special connection.
Don't try to
make it sound dirty!
[LUCY] So, uh what's this
about a "cross-dressing geezer"?
[NATSU]
Remember that creepy,
old man we met back
on Galuna Island?
Well he can disguise
himself as a hot chick!
[HAPPY] What if she really is
a hot chick and the old man
was the disguise?
Nah, I'm tellin' ya,
he's definitely got a
Master Bob-like vibe to him.
That "she" is a "he."
Yikes.
I sure hope Gray
doesn't hit on him.
[LUCY] We've got
more important things
to worry about right
now, you guys.
[jackhammer drilling]
[LUCY] What the heck
are you doing, Virgo?
Well, what does it
look like, Princess?.
I'm making pitfalls in case
the enemy gives chase.
[LUCY]
No, I get that.
But why the swimsuit?
I thought it would be fun
to spice things up a little.
[LUCY]
For who?
[HAPPY]
'Scuse me, Lucy.
I don't mean to be rude but
we've got more important things
to worry about right now
than Virgo's outfit.
You have no right to talk, cat!
Offense or defense?
We've gotta pick one.
So what's our strategy, guys?
It'd be a lot easier to
figure out if you'd stop
goofing off and
get serious, Lucy.
Don't you dare
try to blame me!
Would you like
me to punish her?
Butt out!
Ice Make: Hammer!
[ULTEAR]
Into the future!
[GRAY]
Damn it.
My ice attacks are completely
useless against her!
Well, what did you expect?
[ULTEAR]
I mastered Arc of Time.
To kill a Maker magic wizard.
[ULTEAR]
My mother.
My entire life I've
wanted nothing more than
to do away with her.
You're sick.
You'd kill your own mother?
[ULTEAR] I've never
stopped hating her.
Nice try.
Now, Flash Forward!
But why?
I know Ur cared for you!
Did she?
She used to cry because she
couldn't tell you how she felt!
[ULTEAR] Resorting to
brute force now that
your ice is useless?
[GRAY] No, I'll
beat you with ice.
You just watch.
I'm gonna bring you
down with Ur's magic.
But that's impossible.
Arc of Time magic controls
an object's flow of time.
[ULTEAR] Ice sent to its future
sublimates and sent to its past,
becomes water.
[GRAY]
I can do it.
Because I believe
in Ur's Maker magic.
[ULTEAR] Very well, don't say
I didn't try to warn you.
You cannot defeat me, Gray.
Not with your
pathetic Maker Magic.
[UR and GRAY] I'll free
you from the darkness.
[UR and GRAY]
I'll seal it away...
...forever!
[ULTEAR] I told you,
your ice won't work!
[ULTEAR]
What happened?
I can't control its time!
What the hell's going on?
It's over because you
can't control the time
of living things.
[ULTEAR]
No. That's not ice.
[ULTEAR] He's
frozen his own blood!
Ice Blade.
Seven Strike Dance!
[ULTEAR] Losing the battle
just to win the war.
Such tenacity.
[ULTEAR]
Even so.
I swear.
[ULTEAR]
I won't lose this battle!
No way!
That stance!
[ULTEAR]
I can't!
Not before I've reached
the Grand Magic World!
[ULTEAR]
Ice Make.
Rosenkrone!
[GRAY] She's using the exact
same maker magic as Ur!
[UR] Out of all the magical
arts, I feel this one gives you
the most creative freedom.
Every wizard who
practices Maker magic
has their own unique style.
If you train hard.
Then someday.
You'll create
a style all your own.
[GRAY]
That spell.
I never thought
I'd see it again.
[GRAY]
It was hers.
You used Ur's magic.
I guess it's only
natural since her blood
is flowing
through your veins.
Shut up!!
I'll show you!
Let go!
[GRAY] How the hell did you
become such an evil person?!
What's wrong with you?
Like you care!
You could never understand
what I've been through!
[ULTEAR]
My mother!
That witch abandoned me!
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Momma.
Where are we going?
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Momma.
Where'd you go?
[ULTEAR] My mother,
Ur abandoned me.
[OFFICER A]
Young lady.
I ask that you
please come with us.
[ULTEAR]
Suddenly.
I found myself in
this strange place.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Where'd my momma go?
[OFFICER A] She's gone
home but don't be afraid.
She brought you here
because she knew we would
take good care of you, and help
strengthen your magic power.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Where are we?
[OFFICER B] The Bureau
of Magical Development.
[OFFICER C] It's a marvelous
facility that devises all sorts
of magic spells.
[OFFICER A]
Please Step into your room.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
But.
[OFFICER B] I know you
want to see your mother but
we cannot allow that until your
magic power has grown stronger.
[OFFICER C] In fact,
that was her request.
[OFFICER A] There's a change of
clothes waiting for you inside.
We'll be back shortly.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Why momma?
Why'd you leave me
with these people?
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
I wanna go home.
[OFFICER A]
Miss.
[ALL TOGETHER]
It's time.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
I'm scared.
What're you gonna do?
Please let me go!
[OFFICER A] We're going to
strengthen your magic power.
[OFFICER B] Now this
might hurt a little,
but we need you to stay strong.
[OFFICER C] Remember,
you're doing this for
your mother's sake.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Momma!
[sobbing]
[ALL TOGETHER]
It's time.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
No.
I don't wanna.
[ALL TOGETHER]
It's time.
[BRAIN]
How's she doing?
[OFFICER A] She's a
remarkable vessel, Sir.
All of our previous test
subjects pale in comparison.
That's excellent news.
But no surprise, she's the
daughter of Ur who's said to be
nearly as powerful as
the Ten Wizard Saints.
[BRAIN] Take it up to five
hundred percent and perform
magic infusion
at hourly intervals.
Don't ease up
even if she screams.
[OFFICERS]
Yes, Sir!
[sobbing]
I wanna go home.
Please come and get me.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Momma.
Momma!
[OFFICER B] Subject
three-three-seven-three
has escaped!
[OFFICER C] A sudden spike in
magic power's been detected!
[OFFICER A]
What are you orders, Sir?
[BRAIN] I suppose we can
just let her go for now.
[BRAIN] The real show is still
to come, young daughter of Ur.
Momma. I'm coming
[ULTEAR] The Bureau's constant
magic amplification experiments
had left my mind and my tiny
body completely battered.
[ULTEAR] The only thing that
kept me going was my desire
to see my mother again.
[ULTEAR]
However.
Nothing could've
prepared me for what I saw.
[ULTEAR] There was my mother,
with a smile on her face.
[ULTEAR] Not only
had she abandoned me,
but she was living
with two little boys.
[ULTEAR]
And she looked so happy.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Unforgivable.
[ULTEAR] I decided to go back
to the Bureau and continue
the magic
amplification experiments.
[ULTEAR]
I wanted to grow stronger.
So I could take
revenge on my mother.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Unforgivable.
[BRAIN]
Is there something wrong?
[OFFICER A]
Well, Sir.
[OFFICER B] Her magic power
has been increasing at
an alarming rate over
the past several days.
[OFFICER C] I'm afraid
it's simply too dangerous
to continue.
This child's full
of untapped potential.
I thought she might be one
of the five, brave warriors
I'm searching for but it
doesn't appear that way.
[BRAIN] Unfortunately, her magic
is of a different quality.
I doubt a body link
would be possible.
[BRAIN] I want you to increase
the power to maximum level.
[OFFICER B]
But Sir, if we do that
we risk overloading
the system.
[BRAIN] Do it!
This place can crumble
to the ground for all I care.
I already have
all the spells I need.
[BRAIN] I'll leave Ur's daughter
to him as a parting gift.
[OFFICER A]
He vanished?
[OFFICER C]
Hey! We've got trouble!
[OFFICER B] The magic
power's reversed flow!
[OFFICER A]
It's going to explode!
Evacuate! Evacuate!
[ULTEAR] Eventually,
I learned of the legendary
black wizard Zeref.
And the dark guild, Grimoire
Heart, who sought after him.
[HADES] The Grand Magic World
is dependent upon His revival.
It cannot become
reality without Lord Zeref.
What's the "Grand Magic World"?
A realm where wizards
are free to use any magic
they want, light or dark.
Nothing's off limits,
not even the forbidden magic
that can retrieve
lost happiness.
[YOUNG ULTEAR]
Retrieve lost happiness?.
You can do that with magic?
[HADES]
Yes, with the Arc of Time.
It's rather complicated
but I'm sure you could learn
to master it.
[HADES] It is one of the ancient
and forgotten Lost Magics,
which are now forbidden because
of their immense power.
In this world, it is
considered imperfect.
However, that shall change
in the Grand Magic World.
There, the Arc of Time
will be perfect.
And then the wizard who
masters it will become
a time traveler.
[ULTEAR]
If we succeed.
I can start all over again.
I'll have the chance
to change my cursed life
into one of happiness!
[ULTEAR] I will bring about
the Grand Magic World!
[UR]
Please help me!
[ULTEAR] That voice!
Where's it coming from?
[UR]
I need help!
Please, I'm begging you!
[ULTEAR]
There it is again.
[UR] My daughter's suffering
because she was born with
too much magic power!
[ULTEAR]
My mother.
This must be her memory.
[UR] There's so much of it
condensed into her tiny body
that her fevers won't go away!
[DOCTOR] Don't worry ma'am,
I know of a facility
that specializes in such cases.
[ULTEAR]
My mother's memories.
But why am
I seeing them now?
[ULTEAR]
On Galuna Island,
my mother melted and
flowed into the sea.
[ULTEAR]
The sea.
I can feel her.
She's all around me.
[UR]
My baby.
What the hell did
you monsters do to her?
She's dead?
[UR]
How did this happen?
There's nothing
more for me to say.
[UR] I was told that your agency
specializes in cases like hers.
The only reason I brought
her here is 'cause I thought
you could cure her.
Now she's dead?!
[OFFICER A]
We offer our condolences.
Her magic power,
was simply too strong.
[OFFICER B] It proved
too much for even us to handle.
[BRAIN] It'd be best
for you not to see her remains.
[UR] That's all
you have to say?
No, wait!
Please give
my daughter back to me!
No, she can't be gone!
She can't!!
[ULTEAR]
It's different.
[ULTEAR] Her memory is
so different from mine.
[GRAY]
Ice Make.
Gungnir!
Ur told us about you.
But the memories were
way too painful for her.
[UR] When my daughter
was born it suddenly felt
as though there was a brilliant
light shining in my heart.
One look and I just knew
that she had a bright future
awaiting her.
Back then I was so happy.
Packed inside her tiny body
were limitless possibilities
for the future.
[UR]
The power of life.
My eyes overflowed
with tears of joy that
couldn't be stopped.
[ULTEAR] All I wanted
was to bring about
the Grand Magic World.
[ULTEAR] So I could go back to a
time before I hated my mother.
[UR]
My daughter.
She's proof of my own life.
She's my tears.
Urtear.
[ULTEAR] All I wanted was
to see my mother again and
to tell her that
I loved her one last time.
[ULTEAR] I guess this
means it's over for me.
My battle.
[GRAY] I wish I could say the
same but mine's just startin'.
[ULTEAR]
Be careful.
You can't defeat
Hades on your own.
[GRAY]
I figured as much.
But I'm not alone.
[HAPPY] The weather's turned
stormy all of a sudden!
[NATSU]
Cool!
The rain will set the tone
for the dramatic climax!
I'm fired up now!
[HAPPY] I thought you were gonna
be bummed 'cause if it pours
your power'll be cut in half!
[NATSU] Crap, I didn't
think about that!
Well I won't let some lousy
rain put my fire out!
[HAPPY] Ah, I see
what you did there!
That was pretty clever, Natsu!
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next time: "Rolling Thunder"!
[NATSU] This is gonna be
a big battle so we'd better
hold off on the comedy.
[HAPPY]
Get over yourself!
I said it was
clever, not comedy!
[NATSU]
Geez!
You don't have to be
so harsh, Furball!