- Narrator:
IN A LAND FAR, FAR AWAY,
LIES THE KINGDOM OF FIORE,
A SMALL PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD IN
EVERY MARKET PLACE,
FOR MOST,
MAGIC IS MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART OF
EVERY DAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART.
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER
INTO MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS
DOT THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE,
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS
LEGENDS HAVE BEEN BORN--
A GUILD THAT WOULD NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Erigor: ( chuckles )
STEP INTO OUR PARLOR,
FAIRY TAIL FLIES.
- Erza: WE'RE NOT THREATENED
BY ANY OF YOU.
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE PLANNING
TO DO WITH LULLABY.
- SHE'S QUEEN OF THE FAIRIES,
TITANIA ERZA!
- CIRCLE OF SWORD!
- ( gasping )
- WHAT IS THAT?
- THE STATION IS
SURROUNDED BY WIND.
- THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'LL BREAK THROUGH
MY MAGIC-SEALING BARRIER.
- Narrator:
THE OSHIBANA TRAIN STATION.
- ( groaning )
- JUST FORGET ABOUT IT, LADY.
I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
THERE'S NO UNDOING
ERIGOR'S BARRIER.
YOU AND YOUR
BUDDIES ARE STUCK.
- Gray: ERZA!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE WITH NATSU.
- WE DECIDED TO SPLIT UP.
NEVER MIND THAT, NOW.
LISTEN, I JUST FOUND OUT
EISENWALD'S REAL
TARGET IS CLOVER,
THE NEXT TOWN UP.
- WHAT?
- ERIGOR'S HEADED TOWARD
THE CONFERENCE AS WE SPEAK.
HE'S PLANNING TO USE
THE LULLABY
TO KILL THE GUILD MASTERS.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?!
- ( whimpers )
- Erza: THERE'S A PROBLEM.
THE STATION IS SURROUNDED
BY A WIND BARRIER.
- Gray: YEAH, I KNOW.
I SAW IT EARLIER.
IF YOU TRY TO BREAK
THROUGH THAT THING,
IT'LL MAKE
MINCEMEAT OUT OF YOU.
- I'VE ALREADY TRIED THAT.
- WHOA, IS YOUR ARM OKAY?
- THAT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
WHAT IS
IS GETTING OUT OF HERE.
WE MUST STOP ERIGOR
BEFORE HE REACHES THE
GUILD MASTERS' CONFERENCE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I REMEMBER THEM TALKING ABOUT
SOMEBODY NAMED KAGE
BACK AT THE PUB.
WE HAVE TO FIND
THAT MAN, GRAY.
HE WAS THE ONE WHO BROKE
LULLABY'S SEAL.
- A DISPELLER, HUH?
A SEAL-BREAKING WIZARD.
HE CAN TAKE DOWN
THE WIND BARRIER.
- Erza: THAT'S WHAT I'M HOPING.
NOW LET'S START SEARCHING.
- Gray: RIGHT.
- Byard: KARACKA.
HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
HIDE BACK THERE?
- I'M SORRY, BUT I WAS SCARED.
- FIND KAGE BEFORE THEY DO.
GO NOW.
- NO, PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME.
YOU KNOW I'M NO GOOD
IN A FIGHT, BYARD.
- CALM DOWN.
IT'S A SIMPLE JOB.
EVEN YOU CAN HANDLE THIS.
- ( gasps )
- Happy: FLAME AND WIND.
- ( Lucy groans )
THIS IS USELESS.
I CAN'T FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
- AYE.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY WE JUST
HEAD BACK TO WHERE ERZA IS?
- ( screams )
- WHOA, WHAT'S
WITH THE CRAZY REACTION?
- ERZA GAVE YOU AN ORDER
TO AFTER THE FAT MAN.
SO YOU-- YOU HAVE
TO DO WHAT SHE SAYS, LUCY.
IGNORING AN ORDER FROM ERZA
IS NEVER A GOOD IDEA.
SHE'S GONNA BE
SUPER ANGRY WITH YOU.
AND IF I HAVE TO
WATCH HER PUNISH YOU,
IT MAY SCAR ME FOR LIFE.
- WHAT KIND OF PUNISHMENT
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT HERE?
HEY, I WAS JUST KIDDING.
I WOULD NEVER GIVE UP
ON A MISSION LIKE THAT.
- THE THOUGHT OF AN ERZA SMACK
DOWN SCARE SOME SENSE INTO YOU?
- SHUT UP, STUPID CAT!
WHY ARE YOU
EVEN FOLLOWING ME?!
- ERIGOR!
COME OUT, COME OUT
WHEREVER YOU ARE!
YOU IN HERE?
- GEEZ, HASN'T HE
EVER HEARD OF USING A DOOR?
- WHERE IS HE?
- NOW THAT ERIGOR'S
MADE IT OUT SAFELY,
THIS KID DOESN'T POSE
MUCH OF A THREAT.
I COULD JUST LET HIM GO,
BUT WHAT WOULD BE
THE FUN IN THAT?
THERE, I'VE WANTED TO DO THAT
FOR A WHILE NOW.
HAD ENOUGH,
FAIRY TAIL INSECT?
- ( grumbling )
NOT YOU AGAIN!
- ( chuckles )
WOW, YOU LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
- OH, SHUT IT, DOGGY.
- GET IT RIGHT.
IT'S KAGE!  THE NAME IS KAGE!
- SAME THING REALLY.
- ANYWAY, I THINK I'VE GOT YOU
ALL FIGURED OUT THIS TIME.
YOU EAT FLAMES
TO INCREASE YOUR POWER.
ISN'T THAT YOUR BIG TRICK?
SHOULDN'T BE HARD
TO STAMP OUT.
- ( grumbling )
NOW I REALLY WANT
TO TEACH YOU A LESSON,
BUT I DON'T HAVE THE TIME!
TELL ME WHERE ERIGOR IS!
- YOU THINK I'M JUST
GONNA TELL YOU THAT?
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW,
THEN YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO BEAT IT OUT OF ME.
KNUCKLE SHADOW!
- SO I GET TO KNOCK YOU AROUND
AND I GET THE INFO I WANT?
THAT'S KILLING TWO BIRDS
WITH ONE STONE.
I'M GETTING ALL FIRED UP.
- ( gasps )
- WHY IS THE BUILDING
SHAKING LIKE THAT?
- HA HA!
- ALL RIGHT, FAIRY.
SNAKE SHADOW!
YOU CAN'T RUN THIS TIME.
THEY'LL TEAR YOU TO PIECES.
- I GOT THIS.
FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
- ( gasps )
IMPOSSIBLE.
HE WAS ABLE TO DEFEAT THEM
WITH ONE SHOT.
SO MUCH POWER.
I DIDN'T THINK WIZARDS
LIKE THIS REALLY EXISTED.
- YOU READY TO TALK?
IF NOT, I'VE GOT A FIREBALL
WITH YOUR NAME ON IT.
- NO.
YOU'RE A MONSTER!
- ( rumbling )
- WAS THAT HIM?
- YES.
- NATSU?
- OH, MAN, LOOK
WHAT YOU MADE ME DO.
I WAS TRYING NOT TO MESS UP
THE WHOLE PLACE THIS TIME.
- ( groans )
- ANYWAY, I FEEL BETTER.
SORRY I HAD TO
TAKE YOU DOWN, DIORAMA.
- I TOLD YOU, IT'S KAGEYAMA.
- WHATEVER,
TELL ME WHERE ERIGOR IS
OR YOU'RE GONNA GET TOASTED.
- ( chuckles )
HE'S LONG GONE,
YOU IDIOT.
HE'S NOT EVEN
IN THIS STATION ANYMORE.
- WHAT?
- Erza: NATSU!
DO NOT HARM HIM!
WE NEED HIM ALIVE.
- WAY TO GO, YOU FIRE FREAK.
- HUH?
( grasps )
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I DID WRONG,
BUT I'M SORRY!
- ( screams )
- YOU WILL DISPEL
THE WIND BARRIER.
AND YOU WILL DO SO
WITHOUT COMPLAINT.
- ( whimpers )
- AAH, JUST DO IT, MAN.
THIS CHICK'S A REAL MONSTER.
- SHUT UP, NATSU!
- UNDERSTOOD?
- FINE, I'LL DISPEL IT.
( groans )
- ( gasps )
- ( groaning )
WHY, KARACKA?
- Byard: IT'S A SIMPLE JOB.
EVEN YOU CAN HANDLE THIS.
- Erza: KAGE!
- Byard: YOU HAVE
TO KILL KAGEYAMA.
- Gray: NO, HE WAS OUR
ONLY WAY OUT OF HERE.
- KAGE, DON'T YOU DARE
DIE ON US.
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
- I THINK WE'RE
LOSING HIM, ERZA.
- YOU'RE THE ONLY
ONE OF US THAT'S ABLE
TO DISPEL
THE WIND BARRIER.
JUST HANG ON.
- ( whimpers )
- ( growls )
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT
TO ONE OF YOUR FRIENDS?
HE'S A MEMBER OF YOUR GUILD!
HE TRUSTED YOU
AND YOU TRIED TO KILL HIM!
HOW COULD YOU?!
- ( grunts )
- IS THAT HOW YOU DARK GUILD
MEMBERS TREAT EACH OTHER?
- PLEASE, KAGE,
JUST STAY WITH US.
- HE'S UNCONSCIOUS.
IT'S JUST NO USE.
- WE CAN'T LET HIM DIE.
HE'S OUR ONLY WAY OUT OF HERE.
- BUT THERE'S NO WAY
HE CAN USE HIS MAGIC
IN THIS CONDITION.
- IF I FORCE HIM TO, HE WILL.
- UM...
BAD TIMING, HUH?
- AYE.
- Narrator:
THIS IS CLOVER CANYON,
A CANYON SO DEEP, MANY BELIEVE
ITS TREACHEROUS WALLS
ACTUALLY RISE UP
FROM THE ABYSS.
THE ONLY WAY ACROSS IS
THIS SINGLE TRAIN LINE.
- I'M SO CLOSE TO CLOVER
AND THE GUILD MASTERS,
I CAN TASTE IT.
AND WHAT'S MORE,
THE MAGIC ENERGY
I USED CREATING
THAT WIND BARRIER
IS ALMOST FULLY RECHARGED.
NOW IT'S TIME.
YOU FOOLS NOT ONLY
TOOK AWAY OUR WORK,
BUT YOU ROBBED US
OF OUR RIGHTS.
AND NOW I'M GOING
TO MAKE YOU PAY.
THE REAPER'S CLEANSING
IS NIGH.
- Lucy: WHAT?
ERIGOR WANTS TO USE LULLABY
ON THE GUILD MASTERS?
- Natsu:
OH, WE HAVE TO STOP HIM.
- Erza:
THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
ERIGOR CUT OFF OUR ONLY MEANS
OF REACHING CLOVER
AND HAS HEADED THERE BY AIR.
- I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
WE COULD CATCH UP TO HIM
ON THE MAGIC-MOBILE,
BUT WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
UNTIL WE FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THIS BARRIER.
- HOW ARE WE GONNA DO THAT?
- SEE, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU TRY TO BUST THROUGH.
- KAGE, WAKE UP.
YOU'RE OUR ONLY HOPE RIGHT NOW.
- I'VE GOT TO TRY
TO BREAK THROUGH!
WE HAVE TO SAVE MAKAROV!
( straining )
( groaning )
- NATSU!
- CUT IT OUT, YOU IDIOT.
OBVIOUSLY, BRUTE FORCE
ISN'T GONNA DO YOU ANY GOOD.
- ISN'T THERE
ANYTHING YOU CAN DO?
IF YOU TRIED FREEZING IT,
MAYBE NATSU CAN MELT IT.
- IF I COULD, I WOULD
HAVE DONE THAT ALREADY.
- ( grunts )
- NATSU! - WOULD YOU
STOP TRYING TO BE THE HERO?
YOU'RE GONNA GET
TORN TO SHREDS!
- DAMN IT, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- I SAID STOP IT!
- CRAP.
- WHAT? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ( cheers )
- WE COULD USE YOUR SPIRITS!
BACK AT EVERLUE'S,
I WAS PULLED
FROM ONE PLACE TO ANOTHER
THROUGH THE SPIRIT WORLD.
- WELL, YEAH,
BUT NORMAL PEOPLE
WOULD SUFFOCATE TO DEATH
IF THEY TRIED THAT.
IT'S HARD TO BREATHE
IN THEIR WORLD.
BESIDES, A CELESTIAL WIZARD
CAN ONLY OPEN A GATE
WHEREVER THEY'RE STANDING.
- HUH? - OKAY, LET ME
SIMPLIFY THIS FOR YOU.
EVEN IF WE COULD PASS
THROUGH THE SPIRIT WORLD,
WE WOULD NEED ANOTHER
CELESTIAL WIZARD
TO OPEN A GATE
OUTSIDE THE TRAIN STATION
FOR US TO PASS THROUGH.
- YOU'RE TOTALLY CONFUSING ME.
JUST HURRY UP AND DO IT.
- BUT I TOLD YOU, I CAN'T.
NOT TO MENTION THE VERY ACT
OF A HUMAN ENTERING
THE SPIRIT WORLD
IS A SERIOUS
BREECH OF CONTRACT.
I DIDN'T CARE WHEN YOU DID IT
BECAUSE IT WASN'T MY KEY.
IT WAS EVERLUE'S.
- I DON'T GET YOUR MAGIC AT ALL.
- EVERLUE'S KEY.  HOLD ON.
( screams )
I JUST REMEMBERED, LUCY.
- REMEMBERED WHAT?
- WHAT I WAS TRYING TO TELL YOU
ON THE WAY HERE!
- Lucy: ON THE WAY HERE?
OH YEAH, YOU MEAN, WHEN YOU
KEPT CALLING ME WEIRD?
- LOOK.
- HOW'D YOU GET YOUR PAWS
ON VIRGO'S KEY?!
DIDN'T ANYONE TEACH YOU
THAT IT'S WRONG TO STEAL THINGS?
- BUT I DIDN'T STEAL IT.
VIRGO ASKED ME
TO GIVE IT TO YOU.
- COME ON, GUYS.
WE'RE WASTING WAY TOO
MUCH OF OUR TIME
LISTENING TO THIS NONSENSE.
- WHO'S VIRGO?
- OH, WASN'T SHE THAT
BIG GORILLA-LOOKING MAID.
- Happy: APPARENTLY,
HER CONTRACT WITH EVERLUE
WAS BROKEN AS SOON
HE WAS ARRESTED.
- Virgo: WHOA.
- BEFORE WE ALL LEFT THAT DAY,
SHE CAME UP TO ME AND
SAID THAT SHE WANTED
TO SIGN A NEW CONTRACT
WITH YOU, LUCY.
- GREAT, I GET
A BIG, UGLY SPIRIT.
ANYWAY, THANKS
FOR LETTING ME KNOW,
BUT I'LL HAVE TO DEAL
WITH HER LATER.
IF YOU DIDN'T REALIZE IT,
RIGHT NOW,
WE NEED TO FIND
A WAY OUT OF HERE.
- BUT--
- SHUT UP!
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST MEOW
LIKE EVERY OTHER CAT?!
- SHE CAN BE PRETTY SCARY, HUH?
- MUST HAVE LEARNED IT
FROM ERZA.
- I'M SORRY.
I JUST THOUGHT THAT SINCE
VIRGO CAN DRILL HOLES,
MAYBE SHE COULD DIG
THROUGH THE GROUND
AND GET US TO THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE BARRIER.
- SHE CAN?
- SERIOUSLY?
- UH...
- YOU'RE RIGHT!  SHE CAN.
YOU'RE SO SMART, HAPPY.
WHY DIDN'T YOU MENTION
THAT SOONER, SILLY KITTY?
- SOMEONE WAS PINCHING MY FACE.
- MY MOST SINCERE, HUMBLE,
HEARTFELT APOLOGIES.
I PROMISE I'LL
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
JUST PLEASE
LET ME HAVE THE KEY.
- GIVE ME SOME FISH
AND ALL IS FORGIVEN.
- I CALL UPON THEE
IN THE WORLD OF
THE CELESTIAL SPIRITS.
AND NOW, I BECKON YOU
TO MY SIDE AT ONCE.
PASS THROUGH THE GATE.
OPEN, GATE OF THE MAIDEN.
VIRGO!
- ( doorbell rings )
- HUH?
- YOU SUMMONED, MISTRESS?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
- WHO ARE YOU?
- YOU SUMMONED, MISTRESS?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
- WHO ARE YOU?
- WHAT'S UP, BURGER.
MAN, YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU LOST SOME WEIGHT.
- MY NAME'S VIRGO.
I APOLOGIZE FOR ANY TROUBLE
I MIGHT HAVE CAUSED YOU.
- SHE DIDN'T JUST
LOSE WEIGHT, NATSU!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN? - SHE'S LIKE
TOTALLY DIFFERENT PERSON.
- I'M A VERY LOYAL SPIRIT
WHO'LL DO ANYTHING
TO PLEASE HER WIZARD.
SO I TRY TO TAKE ON
WHATEVER FORM
I THINK MY WIZARD
WILL FIND MOST APPEALING.
- I DON'T KNOW,
I KIND OF LIKED IT
WHEN YOU WERE ALL
BIG AND TOUGH LOOKING.
- DID YOU REALLY?
WELL, THEN...
I CAN SWITCH BACK
IF YOU LIKE.
- DON'T LISTEN TO HIM!
I'M YOUR WIZARD.
AND I LIKE
THE OTHER FORM BETTER.
- AS YOU WISH, MISTRESS.
- I'M AFRAID WE DON'T
HAVE MUCH TIME.
CAN WE WORK OUT
THE CONTRACT DETAILS LATER?
- OF COURSE, WHATEVER
YOU'D LIKE, MISTRESS.
- DO YOU REALLY HAVE
TO CALL ME MISTRESS?
- WOULD YOU PREFER
I CALLED YOU QUEEN? - NO.
- WHAT ABOUT PRINCESS?
- OH, YEAH, THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
- Gray: PRINCESS? YEAH, RIGHT.
- HURRY IT UP, LADIES.
- YES, SIR.  NOW.
WHOA.
- OH WOW, LOOK AT HER GO.
- NICELY DONE, LUCY.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS,
TIME TO BUST OUT OF THIS JOINT.
- ( Natsu strains )
- Gray: WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- I KNOW HE'S
ONE OF OUR ENEMIES,
BUT I'D FEEL GUILTY IF WE
JUST LEFT HIM HERE TO DIE.
- AND HERE'S WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
- LOOKS LIKE WE MADE IT OUT.
- LET'S HEAD TOWARD CLOVER.
- WHOA, THIS WIND IS CRAZY.
- PRINCESS, I'LL KEEP
YOUR PANTIES FROM SHOWING.
- YOU JUST WORRY
ABOUT YOUR OWN.
- OH WOW.
- IT'S NO USE.
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO CATCH UP TO ERIGOR.
YOU CAN'T STOP US.
WE'VE WON.
- Erza: WHERE'S NATSU?
- HAPPY'S NOT HERE EITHER.
- I SEE THE TOWN UP AHEAD.
A BIT FARTHER
AND I'LL HAVE REVENGE.
- ( Natsu groans )
WE'VE GOT YOU NOW.
DIDN'T KNOW CATS COULD FLY
AT MACH SPEED, DID YOU?
YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, BUT I'M SO TIRED.
I CAN'T FLY.
- DON'T WORRY, BUDDY.
I THINK I CAN
HANDLE IT FROM HERE.
- YOU AGAIN.
YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE
PESKY FAIRY TAIL FLIES.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I'M NOT LETTING
YOU GET PAST ME,
YOU DRESS-WEARING WINDBAG.
- Kageyama: SO TELL ME,
WHY ARE YOU
TAKING ME WITH YOU?
- BECAUSE YOU OBVIOUSLY
NEED A DOCTOR.
AND SINCE
EVERYONE LEFT TOWN,
YOU'LL HAVE TO
SEE ONE IN CLOVER.
TRY AND SHOW SOME GRATITUDE.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY ARE YOU HELPING ME?
WE'RE ENEMIES.
OH, WAIT, I GET IT.
YOU'RE TAKING ME HOSTAGE
SO YOU CAN TRY TO MAKE
A DEAL WITH ERIGOR.
WELL, YOU CAN FORGET IT.
HE COULD CARE LESS ABOUT ME
OR ANY OF HIS MEN.
- GEEZ, LIGHTEN UP, DUDE.
- IF YOU WANT TO DIE,
WE CAN MAKE THAN HAPPEN.
- CHILL, GRAY.
- THERE'S A WHOLE LOT
MORE TO THIS WORLD
THAN JUST LIFE AND DEATH,
YOU KNOW?
YOU SHOULD TRY TO LOOK
FOR THE POSITIVE,
YOU AND YOUR EISENWALD PALS.
- ( screaming )
- Gray: WHAT HAPPENED?
- IT'S OKAY.
EVERYTHING'S FINE NOW.
- I'M SO SORRY.
- COULD YOUR BUTT
BE ANY BIGGER?
- SEXUAL HARASSMENT!
KILL HIM, GRAY!
HE SAID I HAD A BIG BUTT.
- GEEZ.
SO MUCH FOR TRYING TO HAVE
A SERIOUS MOMENT.
- MY VISION
IS GETTING BLURRY.
I MUST HAVE USED MORE
MAGIC ENERGY THAN I THOUGHT.
NATSU, YOU HAVE
TO STOP ERIGOR.
IT'S ALL UP TO YOU NOW.
DON'T LET ME DOWN.
- I'M GONNA BURN YOU
AND THAT STUPID FLUTE OF YOURS
TO A CRISP.
- SO YOU WERE ABLE TO
BREAK THROUGH MY WIND BARRIER.
YOU LITTLE FLIES
CAN BE SUCH A NUISANCE.
NOW GET OUT OF MY WAY, KID,
OR ELSE.
- IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
- IMPOSSIBLE.
HE USES HIS FLAMES
TO JUMP AND TO STRIKE.
I UNDERESTIMATED HIS POWER.
- COME ON!
- THIS MIGHT ACTUALLY
BE A CHALLENGE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP THERE,
YOU COWARD?
COME DOWN HERE AND
FIGHT ME LIKE A MAN.
- DON'T GET TOO COCKY, FLY.
STORM BRINGER!
- ( screams )
- NATSU.
( strains )
( pants )
IT'S NO USE.
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
MAGIC ENERGY.
- ( screams )
- ( laughs ) LET'S SEE YOUR
FIREPOWER GET YOU OUT OF THIS.
- Happy: NATSU!
- MAN, THIS SUCKS.
I WASN'T EXPECTING
THAT AT ALL.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO NOW?
( grunting )
( groans )
SORRY, GRAMPS.
- Macao: COME ON, NATSU.
YOU CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT.
NOW WATCH HOW I DO IT.
SEE?
- OH, THAT'S AWESOME.
- YEAH, IT'S
CALLED PURPLE FLARE.
AND EVEN THOUGH IT'S FIRE,
IT CAN DO A LOT MORE
THAN JUST BURN THINGS.
- HOW COME MY FIRE BURNS
EVERYTHING IT TOUCHES?
- 'CAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO MAKE IT NOT BURN.
YOU GOT TO LEARN THAT
IF YOU WISH FOR IT
DEEP DOWN IN YOUR HEART,
THE FIRE DO EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WANT IT TO.
ONCE YOU'VE MASTERED THAT,
THEN NOT EVEN WIND OR
WATER MAGIC CAN BEAT YOU.
- THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
( screams )
- NATSU!
- THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
( chuckles )
SO THAT'S WHAT YOU
WERE TRYING TO TELL ME.
I THINK I GET IT NOW.
- BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- YOU MUST BE
PRETTY COLD UP THERE
HALF NAKED LIKE THAT.
WANT ME TO WARM YOU UP?
- YOUR FLAMES ARE POWERLESS
AGAINST ME.
- OH, YEAH,
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- STORM WALL!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS KID.
THERE'S NO RHYME
OR REASON TO HIS ATTACKS.
IS THIS WHAT ALL
FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS ARE LIKE?
- ( chuckles )
- ALTHOUGH YOUR
POWERS ARE REMARKABLE,
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE
STILL NO MATCH FOR ME.
ENOUGH OF THIS
CAT AND MOUSE CHASE.
IT'S TIME TO GET SERIOUS.
- I'M READY WHEN YOU ARE.
- STORM MAIL!
HERE I COME.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAN'T HANDLE THE BREEZE?
- COWARD.
YOU JUST HAD TO GO
AND WRAP YOURSELF
IN A WIND BARRIER.
THIS'LL BREAK THROUGH IT.
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT THE--
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID MY FIRE GO OUT?
- JUST AS I SUSPECTED,
YOU'RE COMPLETELY HELPLESS
WITHOUT YOUR FLAMES.
LOOKS LIKE I HAVE
THE UPPER HAND.
- NO WAY!
- UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
THE WINDS OF MY STORM MAIL
ATTACK BLOW OUTWARDLY.
IF YOU GET TOO CLOSE,
IT'LL SMOTHER YOUR FLAMES,
LEAVING YOU
POWERLESS AGAINST ME.
- OH, YEAH!
- FIRE CAN NEVER DEFEAT WIND!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Lucy: OKAY, SO WE'VE ERZA,
NATSU, GRAY, AND ME
ALL ON ONE TEAM.
WE'RE A PRETTY AWESOME
LITTLE MIX, DON'T YOU THINK?
- Mirajane: MOST DEFINITELY.
IN FACT, THE FOUR OF YOU
MAY BE THE BEST TEAM
IN ALL OF FAIRY TAIL.
- WOW, YOU REALLY THINK SO?
OH, I BET IF WE START PICKING UP
A LOT OF JOBS,
I'LL BE FAMOUS
LIKE THEM IN NO TIME.
( giggles )
- Both: NEXT TIME...
- Mirajane:
I WONDER HOW MANY TOWNS
YOUR TEAM IS GONNA DESTROY?
AT LEAST TWO OR THREE,
BUT PROBABLY MORE
LIKE FOUR OR FIVE.
- Lucy: COME ON.
IT'S OUR FIRST JOB.