[HAPPY] We need to get away
from the gate, you guys!
Something's coming!
[LUCY screaming]
Natsu totally
destroyed the gate!
Nice work!
[NARRATOR]
Several days after
the Grand Magic Games'
conclusion...
[YUKINO sighs]
Is it absolutely necessary that
I wear this outfit
to the celebration?
Yeah! 'Cause it looks
amazing on you!
It looks great! Very Flattering!
Hey Mira. Can I
get some help here?
Don't worry. I'd bet you'd
look cute in about anything!
[HAPPY]
The Grand Banquet!
[MALE CITIZEN 199A]
Get a load of this.
Some folks are sayin'
that evacuation the other day
was 'cause there were
dragons attacking the city!
That's ridiculous! Everyone
knows those things ain't real!
[MALE CITIZEN 199C] I dunno.
A lot of people are sayin'
they saw 'em.
It was just those
wizards gettin' outta hand.
It can't be their fault
because the king
is throwing them a huge party
in the royal palace tonight!
[MALE CITIZEN 199C] Oh man.
I wish I could be there!
[MALE CITIZEN 199B]
That's a first!
They've never ended the games
with a big blowout like that.
[MALE CITIZEN 199A]
I guess the king was just
really into it this year.
[LUCY giggling]
[WENDY]
Oh, wow!
Hey, you're here!
Well, let's party!
That get-up's
a little fancy for you.
[GAJEEL grunts]
At least I'm wearing somethin'.
Now be nice. We have to
get along with each other
and our former
competitors as well.
Yeah, well. Tell that to
Natsu when he gets here.
Wonder if he decided
to skip this thing.
This place is loaded
with real man food!
[GRAY]
Aw, yeah!
Look guys! I'm seein' double!
[MACAO]
Hey! We're in the royal palace
so you'd better behave!
And the king is being
extremely generous.
Aye!
We'll see if that
lasts past tonight.
I'm sure these
hooligans will test
the limits of his good nature.
The palace is amazing.
I could see myself
living here someday.
Truly a place of
glimmering beauty.
[HIBIKI, EVE, REN]
Hip Hip Hooray for King Ichiya!
Now men! Let's take it
from the top! Key of B flat!
Top of what?
Uh. Do you know it?
Wanna go another round?
You're on. And I'm
playing to win this time!
[ALL]
Let's get wild!
I can't believe I'm wearing
this ridiculous thing.
How come?
'Cause you look gorgeous!
The gown is quite
stunning on you.
The only way it could
look better is with a smile!
Never thought I'd see
the day the king
would invite me
to a royal shindig!
Old age definitely
has its perks.
[LEVY] We put everything
on the line that day.
July seventh.
We fought dragons,
and guaranteed the
future of the planet!
[GAJEEL]
Yo.
[LEVY]
Hey, Gajeel!
So. Skipping the party
to do a little writing, huh?
[LEVY]
Yeah. Nerdy, right?
[GAJEEL]
Nah. You're just a rebel.
I guess I am. You're lucky
to be alive, ya know?
[GAJEEL]
Nothin's killed me so far.
[LEVY] But taking on a dragon
all by yourself like that
was such a dangerous
thing to do.
I was actually scared
you weren't gonna make it.
[GAJEEL]
You shouldn't worry about me.
Well, I hate
to break it to you,
but that's not really an option.
It's a big 'ol waste
o' time. And annoying.
[LEVY whimpering]
[GAJEEL] What the hell
are ya cryin' for?
I don't exactly
know why. I'm sorry.
[GAJEEL] C'mon, ya don't
have to apologize.
[HISUI]
Hello Lucy!
[LUCY gulps]
Princess Hisui!
[HISUI] I'm glad that
you're enjoying the food.
[LUCY] Probably a little
too much to be honest.
[HISUI giggling]
[HISUI] So you are part of the
illustrious Heartfilia family.
[LUCY giggling] My dad made
quite a name for himself.
Not only that,
but he was actually
a personal friend of mine.
[LUCY gasps]
I had no idea.
[HISUI] Indeed. Which makes
me feel all the worse
for causing you so much trouble.
It's okay. That's the life of
a guild wizard, after all.
If we don't find trouble,
it always finds us.
By the way. I'm surprised
that pink haired boy
from your guild
isn't joining us tonight.
Now that you mention it,
I kind of am too.
[JUVIA]
Gray, my darling!
[JUVIA] I've decided to make
an upgrade. Call it Juvia 2.0.
I'll bet this version
is even crazier
than the last one.
[JUVIA] So. Feast your eyes
on the new and improved
girl of your dreams.
[GRAY groans]
[JUVIA] Now open those
strong arms and embrace me!
[GRAY]
I'll pass.
[JUVIA groans]
Well this is the new and
improved version of me.
The one who isn't
afraid to tell you
exactly what I'm thinkin'.
[JUVIA whimpering]
Oh. My darling is so
bold and brazen and hot!
[GRAY gasps]
She's more insane than ever!
[LYON] You need to treat her
with more respect, Gray!
[GRAY]
What?
That includes respecting
her feelings as well.
And although I do love her,
it's clear she doesn't
feel the same.
[YUKA, TOBY]
Yeah, no duh!
This party is startin'
to get real annoying.
Why does Natsu get to skip it?
[JUVIA] It seems like he
should be here somewhere
causing a ruckus.
[BOTH gasping]
Wow! It's so sparkly!
It looks like a jewel!
Yeah, it's beautiful.
But I wonder
what it tastes like!
[WENDY, SHELIA munching]
So good.
[MAVIS]
Oh, I bet that's yummy.
You're here?
[SHELIA]
Is something the matter?
Uh. No. I'm just fine.
[SHELIA]
Hm?
[WENDY] I kinda forgot that
only people in Fairy Tail
can see Master Mavis.
[MAVIS whining] Can I have
a little bite of that?
I'm not sure that's gonna
work. Do ghosts even eat?
[SHELIA]
Hm?
[WENDY]
Excuse me, First Master,
but have you seen
Natsu tonight?
[MAVIS]
No.
Well, neither have I.
Which is weird
because he's usually
practically impossible to miss.
Wendy! I think there's
something near me
and it wants my food!
Natsu hasn't shown up?
That would explain why things
are relatively peaceful.
[FEMALE 199A]
Oh, you're so strong.
[FEMALE 199B]
Yeah. Such manly muscles.
[FRIED] Girls! Get your
hands off him right now!
That's weird, I guess nobody
has seen him at all today.
I'm sure he's fine.
He'll turn up sooner or later.
He's probably just
sleepin' through it.
[KAGURA gasps]
Ugh. I can hardly walk.
[ERZA] So you were
able to come after all.
On the mend?
[KAGURA]
Yes, thank you.
I have a proposition.
Can we let go of
our past and be friends?
[KAGURA]
No.
[ERZA gasps]
Because I'd rather
be your sister.
Do you mean it? You're
such a little sweetheart!
Hey, would you
please let go of me?
It's embarrassing.
[BETH, ARAÑA laughing]
Come on, I think
you need a hug!
Oh, Millianna. I really wish
that you'd cheer up a bit.
Luckily, I have just the thing.
Here!
Are ya feelin' pumped?
Kitty-kitty!
There's more.
[MILLIANNA squealing] Oh! So
many precious kitties! Meow!
[PANTHERLILY] Hey. We're not
your stuffed animals, you know.
[HAPPY] Aye. You're
squeezing way too hard.
[CARLA] Please! Let go!
[MILLIANNA] Aw, look at
those chubby wubby...
[ERZA] Happy, do you
know where Natsu is?
[HAPPY] No, I honestly
don't have a clue.
His absence is
beginning to worry me.
I hope nothing has happened.
[GAJEEL munching]
All right! I owe Natsu a drink!
It's good stuff. Top shelf.
Huh? Salamander ain't here, pal.
[STING] Aw, man!
After all this fighting,
I was trying to do
something nice for a change.
[LECTOR]
I guess the plan's a bust, then.
[FROSCH]
Well, better luck next time.
[GAJEEL]
Laios.
[ROGUE] If you don't mind,
I'd prefer to be called Rogue.
You need to watch yourself.
The you from the future
was a real piece of work.
Yes. I know.
And that would be putting
it extremely lightly.
I'm not him. I will never
become that man. I swear it.
I know he won't!
[GAJEEL chuckles]
Well, since Natsu
didn't show up.
I guess that
you're close enough.
That's right. Close enough
to knock your teeth in.
Cut him some slack, he's still
pretty new at bein' friendly.
[OLGA] I don't think I've
ever seen him act like this.
If he has, I'd
certainly remember it.
[STING] A toast.
To the Fairies and Tigers!
[STING laughing]
[ALL gasp]
Look who's here!
Sorry. I don't think
I can do this right now.
[STING]
Wait!
[YUKINO gasps]
[STING] Please, stick around
for a little while at least.
The master and milady
are gone for good.
They won't be here.
[LUCY]
Huh?
[STING] Look. I'm sorry
for the way we treated you.
But we're starting
everything over from scratch.
The way we were...
was wrong.
But the old Sabertooth
guild is history now.
From here on out,
we'll be the kind of guild
that treats our
members like family.
Well, then I wish you the best
of luck with all of that.
[STING] I know that
the wounds are still fresh.
But I'd love it if you
were part of it again.
[KAGURA] Are you kidding me?
Don't be such an idiot!
[YUKINO]
Kagura?
Did everybody just forget
that her life is in my hands?
So since I'm the one
making the rules here,
I say she's gotta
join Mermaid Heel.
[ALL]
What?
Huh?
You're completely wasted!
It doesn't matter! She belongs
with us and you can't stop it!
[BOTH growling]
[ERZA]
Stop right there!
We won't stand by
while you decide her fate!
We're manly.
That's right! And if she
chooses to be in any guild
it'd better be ours!
Yeah!
Personally, I think there
are already too many girls
in Fairy Tail to compete
for Gray's attention.
[LISANNA]
And she's too much like me.
Yeah. You're both
the little sister types
with the exact same hair!
I never thought about
joining Fairy Tail.
[EVE] No way. A woman that's
as beautiful as you are.
[HIBIKI] Deserves nothing less
than the most beautiful guild.
[REN]
So join us.
[ICHIYA] You've such
an intoxicating parfum.
We'd love to have you!
If she wants to be
with the best guild,
there's no question she should
become part of Lamia Scale.
[JURA] Let's not get
involved with this.
Get in our guild now!
Don't be rude.
We've always been
totally macho,
but I think Quattro Cerberus
could use a womanly touch!
I know that we lost
the Grand Magic Games,
but there ain't no way in hell
we're gonna lose this battle!
[ALL]
Wild!
Hey! Hold on!
Don't do this!
[MAKAROV]
Time for another Fairy Tail win!
[GOLDMINE]
I'd like to show everybody here
what a wild spirit can do!
[OHBA]
I'll spin you!
[BOB] All these hot-blooded
suitors remind me
of my younger days.
Now the masters
are getting involved?
This is crazy!
That's love for ya!
C'mon!
Manly battle!
Just give up!
Not on your life!
Yank out Makarov's mustache!
Don't you dare, old hag!
[MALE SOLDIER 199A]
Whoa! They're out of control!
[YUKINO whimpering]
[MIRAJANE] Aw, there's
nothing to cry about.
[YUKINO] I know. But all
of you make me so happy.
[MIRAJANE giggles]
It's wonderful to see you smile!
[YUKINO giggles]
[WIZARDS yelling]
[MIRAJANE]
Whatever you choose,
there's definitely
a place for you.
[YUKINO]
Thank you.
Everyone stop! This instant!
[ARCADIOS] In honor
of your performances
during the games,
and for your bravery facing
the greatest danger
this kingdom has ever known.
His majesty would
like to personally deliver
this message to you. Pay heed!
Hi mister king!
Sh.
[ALZACK chuckles]
Huh?
Loyal subjects!
Shut up and listen!
[MATO]
Give me back my crown!
[WIZARDS]
Huh?
All hail King Natsu!
New ruler of Fiore!
[ALL groaning]
Hungry Wolf Knights. Get him.
[KAMA] Sorry, but this
is just too much.
[MAKAROV groaning]
[MATO]
That's enough, okay!
[NATSU] Oh come on! After all,
we won your little games!
[MATO]
Please give it back!
[NATSU] For the rest
of today, I am your king!
Now do what I say!
We should've seen
this one coming.
Aye, sir!
[NARRATOR] We've seen
some fierce competition
over the course of
the Grand Magic Games.
We've also witnessed
an amazing show of solidarity,
as wizards from opposing
guilds banded together
to secure the future
of the kingdom.
And now, they've
gathered once more
in the spirit of
celebration. However...
[JUVIA whimpering]
[FRIED grunts]
[LAXUS gasps]
[FRIED whimpers]
[NATSU munching]
[NATSU gags]
[LUCY]
Here ya go!
[NATSU gulps]
Did you forget to chew?
[HISUI]
Father.
[NATSU, LUCY]
Huh?
[TOMA]
Hisui.
I beg your forgiveness.
My actions brought
shame to the kingdom.
Once the festivities are over,
I will accept whatever
punishment you see fit.
But, Princess...
[ARCADIOS]
Please wait.
[HISUI]
Colonel Arcadios.
With all due respect,
I must intercede
on the Princess's behalf.
The Eclipse began as
a means to defeat Zeref.
The debacle with
the Eclipse Two was
the result of that time
traveler's deception.
Due to his other
accurate predictions.
She was led to believe
it was the only way
to save Fiore
from total annihilation.
[DARTON] That's true.
Her intentions were pure.
All for the sake of the kingdom.
Darton...
[LUCY]
It was more than that!
[ALL grunt]
The princess did
whatever she could
to protect the future
of the entire world!
[ERZA] Yes. She has
done nothing wrong.
She had the best
intentions in mind.
I implore you to forgive
her transgressions.
Punish her or not, it won't
change what happened.
Besides, she was
able to get every wizard
in Fiore to work as a team.
Aye, sir!
Yeah. That's a good point.
If not for the
princess's actions,
Fiore may have very well
remained a kingdom divided.
[HISUI gasps]
Thank you.
Gray and I had drifted apart.
But now we're two
hearts beating as one!
Can you please contain
your insanity for a second?
It's true. We've all
gained so much from this.
Yes. Notably, a new
sense of purpose.
Yeah! I think so, too!
Things are awesome.
I mean, even the
knuckleheads in Sabertooth
have started gettin' along.
Listen everyone!
By the power vested in me!
I declare the princess
not guilty!
She makes the rules
far as I'm concerned.
[BETH, ARAÑA] That's right!
[MILLIANNA] Meow!
You should probably
stay out of this.
You're way too drunk
to be in this conversation!
What did you say?
Are y'all tryin' to tell
Kagura what to do?
Silence! You are in the
presence of His Majesty!
[WIZARDS gasping]
I have considered
all of your arguments.
However, she is accountable.
[ARCADIOS] Your majesty.
I will accept all of the blame!
Majesty. I am the one who
should be punished for this.
You should just go ahead
and punish all of us, too!
[TOMA]
Arcadios' loyalty to Hisui,
and Darton's loyalty
to the kingdom,
these both please me greatly.
But what pleases
me most of all...
...are the brave
wizards assembled here
that work tirelessly for peace.
Father...
In light of all this,
I've conceived a
suitable punishment.
[TOMA] You must wear the
pumpkin head for an entire week!
Huh?
[ARCADIOS] Your Majesty.
This is the punishment?
[DARTON] This is all
she's required to do?
A dose of humility.
Once this week is over,
the slate will be clean.
My sweet Hisui.
[ARCADIOS]
Hm.
[DARTON chuckles]
That's wonderful.
Aren't you happy?
Yes Punkin.
[WIZARDS laughing]
They've grown so strong.
[MAKAROV grunts]
The weight of the world
will be safe on their shoulders.
Yes.
Listen. I'd like to
thank you for everything
you've done, punkins.
This has gotta be just a
little embarrassing. Punkin!
Naw. It seems like a lot
of fun to me. Punkin!
Aw. Yeah, I think
so too, punkin!
[TOMA] I do have extras
if you'd like to wear one, too!
[NATSU, LUCY, HAPPY]
Huh?
[LUCY giggles]
[HAPPY laughs]
[NATSU giggles]
[NATSU, HAPPY, LUCY]
Pumpkin party!
[WIZARDS laughing]
[HAPPY] Hey Natsu,
have you thought about
what you wanna do
when we get back home?
[NATSU] I wanna go on
a bunch of awesome jobs!
[HAPPY] I think I'd
rather go fishing!
[NATSU] Oh yeah, we haven't
done that in forever!
[HAPPY] I totally found
the world's best fishing spot
a while ago. The biggest
one there was humongous!
I wanna get him
in my belly so bad!
[NATSU] Sounds like fun to me!
Mind if I tag along with ya?
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next Time: Droplets of Time!
[NATSU] I gotta wonder
how things are going
back in ol' Magnolia.
[HAPPY] I bet they'll all
be happy when the Champs
of the Grand Magic Games
are back in town!