[HAPPY] Hey, Lucy,
you feeling any better?
Where are we?
[PANTHERLILY] Not sure.
[GAJEEL yelling]
[blows landing]
Well, this got
boring in a hurry.
You're just wasting
my time, kid.
I'm outta here.
[ROGUE] You don't scare me...
[ROGUE] You aren't even
as strong as Natsu Dragneel.
The hell you say?
[FUTURE LUCY] To
make matters worse,
we're going to be stuck
behind bars until it happens.
[HAPPY] Whaddya mean "it"?
[WENDY] So, uh, what made
you decide to risk your life
and come here from the future?
[FUTURE LUCY] To change the
horror that is my past.
Why's it so awful?
Tell us. Maybe we
can help and at least
you won't have to
do it all by yourself.
[FUTURE LUCY whimpers quietly]
[FUTURE LUCY] Our
worst nightmares
are about to come to life...
A swarm of more than
ten thousand dragons
are going to attack the kingdom.
The city will burn,
the castle will fall...
And countless lives
are going to be lost.
[ALL gasp]
[HAPPY] Frog!
[DARTON clears throat]
The kingdom is going to be
attacked by a swarm of dragons?!
That's what I was told,
but to be honest,
I find it hard to believe.
I won't believe it.
Not until I see how the
Grand Magic Games play out.
We're...
so...
dead!
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] No way!
[PANTHERLILY] Be quiet, please.
More than ten
thousand dragons...
But I thought they
were all extinct.
They're gonna tear
us all to shreds!
Hey, do you think this
could have something to do
with that dragon grave?
I was wondering
that myself...
Well, now that you
mention it...
Seriously! They're
gonna rip us apart!
Pipe down!
You'd think we could
sense that many dragons...
It's possible we
haven't noticed them
because they're
laying low,
waiting for the perfect
time to strike.
We can't just sit around
and wait for that to happen!
We're gonna have to fight 'em!
You gotta be kiddin' me!
We can't take on
that many dragons!
You mean... you
actually believe me?
Wait, you were lyin'?!
[FUTURE LUCY] No!
I would never lie to you!
It's just that I
honestly didn't think
you were going to believe me.
I'm surprised, that's all.
You're one of us, which means
we don't have any
reason to doubt you.
[FUTURE LUCY giggles]
You really need to get
it together, future me.
Don'tcha think you should have
more faith in your friends?
[FUTURE LUCY] Am I
seriously lecturing myself?
But I guess you've
got a good point.
[CARLA thinking] Now it's
all coming together...
Mercurius crumbling...
Lucy singing
inside the castle...
Wait, she wasn't singing...
She must have been crying!
But why? What could've happened?
[CARLA] Excuse me. If
I'm not mistaken, we're still
inside the castle when
the dragons attack.
What happens to us?
[WENDY] I'm scared.
I don't think I wanna know.
I've got a feeling we
won't like her answer.
[NATSU] You don't think...
we're gonna end up goners?
[MIRAJANE] Oh, my...
No, that can't be right.
Are we really gonna die?
[YUKINO thinking] Once
again, I bring misfortune
to everyone around me...
[explosions]
[DRAGONS roaring]
[roaring]
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY] No! Natsu!
[FUTURE LUCY] I'm
afraid I don't remember
what day it was.
But when I came to...
I knew I had no choice
but to use the Eclipse.
I had no idea
how to operate it,
but I was somehow
able to get it open...
I was determined to go back
in time and warn someone.
[FUTURE LUCY] I
was desperate...
I doubted whether it would
work, but I had to try.
And then suddenly
it was July fourth.
of the year seven-ninety-one.
Hey, wait a second, but that
was just a few days ago!
Does that mean
it's only capable
of making small
jumps back in time?
[WENDY] But I thought it
was supposed to go back
four-hundred years
to defeat Zeref?
[FUTURE LUCY] I don't
know all the details...
Maybe it was broken,
so it wasn't able to take
me back that far in time.
[ARCADIOS thinking] It
all makes sense now...
This girl is the mysterious
person from the future
who advised the princess.
Something's not
right... I can feel it...
[FUTURE LUCY] If you make
it out of the castle,
you'll need to rendezvous
with Jellal, but be careful
because there are
lacrimas all over the city
monitoring the games.
That means you'll have to
take an underground route
to meet with him.
How is he involved?
[FUTURE LUCY] I've
explained everything to him
as best I can...
I'm sure that he's busy coming
up with a plan as we speak.
Why's he coming
up with the plan?
[FUTURE LUCY] It's my fault.
I'm really sorry.
I probably should've come here
with some sort of strategy...
But, to be honest. I don't know
what we can do to prevent it.
I needed his help.
[ARCADIOS thinking]
Just as I thought...
[ARCADIOS] Princess?!
Did you say "from the future"?
[HISUI] Yes. I know it
sounds insane but hear me out.
They said here's another
way to use the gate.
They called it "Eclipse Two".
[ARCADIOS] There is?
What does it entail?
I don't know if you
are aware of this,
but for the last seven years
we've used the games to store
magic power within this gate.
The magic we've accumulated
within that time is now
as powerful as an
Etherion blast.
What?!
It's on par with the sacred
light of the Magic Council?!
But it's said that a
single Etherion blast
can destroy an entire nation!
[HISUI] This wealth of
magic power is the core
of the Eclipse Two.
And we shall unleash it
onto the swarm of dragons.
[ARCADIOS thinking]
I don't understand...
She's got to be the one
who told the princess
about the Eclipse Two...
which means she's lying
about arriving on the fourth.
Why would she choose
to deceive her friends?
I'm really sorry, you guys.
I hope you can forgive me.
I know I should've
found you sooner.
But I was just at a
complete loss on what to do
besides just trying to warn you.
[NATSU] Chin up...
There's no need
for you to apologize.
I'd like to thank you.
You risked your life
for us; for our future.
[FUTURE LUCY sobs]
[WENDY giggles]
[LUCY] Hm...
[NATSU] We're gonna
find a way to stop 'em.
You just watch.
[ULTEAR] What do you mean
it's not necessarily true?
Oh, come on!
You don't honestly think
Lucy could be lying to us?
Why would she
do such a thing?
[JELLAL] More than
ten thousand dragons.
The Eclipse...
That strange magic power...
The pieces of the puzzle
just don't fit together.
What are you saying?
That she may have some
ulterior motive in crafting
this version of the future.
I'm not sure whether
this Lucy's words are false
or whether her entire being
is actually a fabrication.
[ROGUE panting]
Aw man, my ears must
be playin' tricks on me.
Coulda swore you said
I'm not as strong as Natsu.
[FROSCH] Poor Rogue...
[ROGUE laughs]
What's funny?
I always wondered why you
decided to join Fairy Tail.
It's taken me a while,
but I think that I've
finally figured it out.
[GAJEEL] Oh yeah?
Let's hear it.
[ROGUE] You've probably
forgotten all about it by now,
and I don't blame you because
it was such a long time ago.
[ROGUE] I was just
a kid back then.
A snot-nosed punk who looked up
to your guild, Phantom Lord.
As a kid, my biggest
dream in life was to
become a member of that
guild when I grew up.
Unfortunately, I never
got the chance...
They were forced to
disband when they
challenged Fairy Tail and lost.
And of all the guilds
you could have joined,
you chose the
most despicable.
You joined Fairy Tail.
[ROGUE] I was absolutely
heartbroken...
I couldn't believe that you
would pick the scoundrels
who destroyed Phantom Lord.
I was so confused...
Deep down I knew there
had to be a reason,
but I couldn't figure
it out for the life of me.
[ROGUE] That is, until now...
You wanted friends...
didn't you?
[ROGUE] The very
notion of friendship
doesn't exist in Sabertooth.
We were nothing but our
master's foot soldiers.
Forced to his follow
his orders, or else.
If we were defeated,
he'd make us pay.
When you're in a guild,
you don't ever.
turn your back on friends.
[ROGUE] I don't really know
what it's like to be in a guild
because I don't have friends.
I'm so lost...
I have no idea what I've been
fighting for all of this time.
[ROGUE] I've realized
that friendship
is what makes your
guild so powerful.
That's why we
never measured up.
The only exceptions are M'lady,
who's unbelievably strong...
And Sting, whose true power
awoke for Lector's sake.
[GAJEEL] Dumbass.
That's the biggest load
of bull I've ever heard.
[GAJEEL chuckles]
Sure looks like you
got a friend to me.
That frog.
What frog?
Hey, I think he's
talkin' about me!
Frosch is a cat,
you idiot!
Well, If you wanna get
technical, he's an Exceed.
Ain't he?
[ROGUE] You know, you're
right. Frosch is my friend.
Your best friend!
Thanks for reminding
me of that.
[VOICE] Rogue...
[VOICE] Face forward.
That man standing
in front of you?
He is your enemy.
Where is that voice
coming from?!
[GAJEEL] Uh... You okay, kid?
[VOICE] Rogue...
You must kill Gajeel.
Who are you?! And
why can't I see you?!
[VOICE] You have
to kill him.
It is your destiny.
[ROGUE] Show yourself!
[VOICE] You fool.
[VOICE] That's right.
I am your shadow.
[SHADOW ROGUE] I'll lend
you my strength...
Now go, and
strike him down.
It's this way!
You wanna tell us how you knew
about this underground path?
I spent some time
exploring the castle
so I'd know how to get us outta
here without being caught.
It's the least I could do.
Well played, Miss.
Future Lucy's way
smarter than the normal one.
[MIRAJANE] We need to hurry
and fire the signal flare.
Yeah, no kidding!
I'll bet the others
are worried sick by now.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIER A] There they are!
[SOLDIER B] Capture
the fugitives!
[SOLDIER C] Let's get 'em, men!
The royal army?!
I swear I didn't know they
were stationed here, you guys!
What'll we do?!
We show 'em who's boss!
We've got magic so they don't
stand a chance against us!
Ain't that the truth!]
[WENDY] We've got a problem!
Colonel Arcadios
is missing!
Yukino's gone too!
What?
But they were both right
behind us just a second ago!
Arcadios is one thing,
but we can't leave Yukino...
I'm going back for her!
[PANTHERLILY] Hey, wait!
[LUCY] We need to
stick together!
I'll come back as
soon as I find her!
We're countin'
on ya, Mira...
'Kay, you ready
for this, buddy?
Hell yeah...
[BOTH] Let's kick some ass!
[SOLDIER D] Now, men! Attack!
[NATSU shouting]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[WENDY thinking] Please...
Be careful, Mira...
[LUCY thinking] I hope
Yukino's okay...
Don't you worry about a
thing; I'm here to protect you!
[CARLA thinking] I've got
this strange feeling...
If only there was
something I could do...
[ROGUE grunting]
[GAJEEL] Hey, man.
Are you feelin' alright?
[SHADOW ROGUE]
Go on and kill Gajeel.
You must... For it
is my destiny.
[ROGUE grunting]
What the hell's
gotten into you?
[SHADOW ROGUE] I'll lend
you my strength.
[ROGUE screaming]
Gajeel!
[MAN A] What brought that
on all of a sudden?!
[MAN B] I dunno!
Did he say somethin' to offend
him?
You don't wanna
mess with me.
This is the kind of power that
we can wield together, Rogue.
So let us strike him down
without any more hesitation!
Who are you?!
[SHADOW ROGUE] Who am I?
One who controls
destiny: A shadow.
[GAJEEL] What kinda
nonsensical crap is that?!
[GAJEEL grunts]
I dunno what your
deal is, pal,
but it sounds like you wanna
do some real fightin'...
Bring it on.
I don't understand
why they're fightin'
all of a sudden; I thought
they'd just made peace.
There's definitely
something strange going on.
Come on! Wipe the
floor with that jerk!
Iron Dragon Sword!
[GAJEEL grunts]
Shadow Dragon
Waxwing Flash.
This is awful!
Why, Rogue...?
What's with you?!
[GAJEEL] Where'd he go?!
[SHADOW ROGUE]
Right behind you.
Shadow Dragon Slash!
What's happening,
First Master?!
He's been possessed by
someone or something.
[GAJEEL grunting]
What?! But Gajeel grabbed
him in shadow form a second ago!
[LEVY] It's almost like
his magic is changing.
[MAVIS thinking] This magic...
It's an incredibly evil power...
In all my years, I've
never seen anything like it.
[SHADOW ROGUE]
Rogue was right...
You're not nearly as
strong as Natsu Dragneel.
That's what
you think, bub.
[SHADOW ROGUE] I'm merely
speaking the truth...
Not that Natsu Dragneel
is any match for me.
Do you feel
that power?!
I definitely do!
[ULTEAR] It's coming
from the city.
[JELLAL] Calm down...
The future Lucy has been
caught in the fighting
so we must tread carefully.
As long as Natsu's
group is with her,
there's no need to act rashly.
[PANTHERLILY] Be careful, Lucy!
I'll be fine!
[WENDY shouts]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
These kids are a lot stronger
than I thought they were!
[SOLDIER F] Better call
the Anti-Magic Squad!
[SOLDIER G] Can't let these
brats get the best of us!
[NATSU shouting]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[NATSU grunts]
[MAGIC SOLDIER A] A direct hit!
[MAGIC SOLDIER B] Waves two
and three, be prepared to fire!
[CARLA] Did they
just use magic?!
[HAPPY] It sure looked like it!
Who are they?!
They must be some kind
of specialized unit!
[NATSU] Ya caught me off guard.
With magic that weak, I wouldn't
quit your day job, guys.
[MAGIC SOLDIER C] It had
no effect!
[MAGIC SOLDIER B] Is this
kid some kind of a monster?!
[MAGIC SOLDIER A] So what now?!
[VOICE] Heya! Sorry
for the wait, gentlemen!
Not you again!
We don't need
your help!
[MAGIC SOLDIER B] Yeah, get
lost, ya dolphin-lovin' freak!
[NATSU] Who are you
just bustin' in here?!
I swear it wasn't
on porpoise!
Who am I?
The hottest magic soldier the
Kingdom of Fiore has to offer.
And he's really heavy!
What is the deal
with this guy?
Do you think he's a wizard?
Or is he a celestial spirit?
Never seen a
spirit like that.
Is it punishment
time yet, Princess?
Now behold my magnificence
as I dive headlong
into battle for lovely
Princess Hisui!
My ball! Gimme that!
[MAGIC SOLDIERS yelling]
Why'd that weirdo
take out his men?
That is one
angry-lookin' fishie!
It's not a fish,
it's a mammal.
[NATSU grunting]
Wow, you're pretty strong
for an overgrown tuna!
[DOLPHIN] We might
not be the smartest,
but we got plenty of stamina!
Oh, yeah? Your
buddy's out cold.
I can't go on. Sorry!
Seriously?!
[NATSU] Alrighty then.
If you're the hottest,
then the heat I throw at
you should be no problem!
Go ahead and
do your worst;
a warrior like me ain't
afraid of a little fire!
Geez, You're
sweating buckets!
[NATSU] Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
[BOTH] What a terrible FIN-ale!
[CROWD mumuring]
[GAJEEL grunting]
[SHADOW ROGUE laughs]
It's hard to believe that
I once looked up to you...
How pathetic.
[GAJEEL groans]
He's gonna end up killing
him if he doesn't let go!
Gajeel!
[FROSCH] I gotta help him...
I gotta get Rogue back
before it's too late!
[SHADOW ROGUE]
It won't be long until
the shadows have eaten you away.
Once they've had their fill,
this world will be free of you.
You'll vanish. Forced to
sleep in eternal darkness.
[GAJEEL chuckles]
[GAJEEL] If Salamander
can pull it off,
then I sure as hell can too.
[SHADOW ROGUE] What?!
[GAJEEL laughs]
What have you done?!
[LEVY] No way...
He ate the shadows?!
That's one of the most
impressive feats I've seen.
He used his power to consume
and absorb the shadow.
[GAJEEL] I dunno who you are,
but you better get out
of his body, or else!
[SHADOW ROGUE] You want
me to leave Rogue?
[GAJEEL] You'd think you'd get
to know more about the kid
before you go and possess him.
His name ain't Rogue,
it's Raios;
and he's my sworn brother.
[GAJEEL] You can say you looked
up to me all you want...
But you know as well as
I do that ain't the truth...
'cause I wasn't that
kinda guy back then.
Be honest
with yourself.
You didn't look up to me,
you feared me.
I was never afraid...!
[GAJEEL] Maybe you forgot
'cause I'm such a
nice guy these days...
But I'll make you
remember your fear!
I don't believe it...
An Iron Shadow Dragon?!
[NATSU] Whoa! Did ya see that?!
Gajeel went and ate a shadow!
[HAPPY] Like you have
any right to talk!
You eat fire,
for cryin' out loud!
[NATSU] So? Munchin'
on fire is nothin'
like gobblin' up a shadow!
Fire is for eatin'
and it tastes great!
[HAPPY] I guess I
can't argue with ya
since I've never tasted it...
[NATSU] I just don't get
why anyone would ever
wanna eat a shadow.
It's weird, y'know?
[HAPPY] I don't really
think it's any weirder
than eatin' fire.
[HAPPY &amp; NATSU] Next time:
Roaring Thunder!
[NATSU] Tell you what, how
'bout I take you to a place
where you can eat
some amazing fire?
[HAPPY] Thanks, Natsu,
but I think I'll pass.