- Narrator: IN A
LAND FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE,
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME, BOUGHT AND
SOLD IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST,
MAGIC IS NEARLY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER
INTO MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS
DOT THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS
LEGENDS HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WILL
NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY ON FAIRY TAIL...
- Mira:
WELCOME TO THE GUILD, LUCY.
- AAH!
- STOP FIGHTING!
- SO NATSU'S FINALLY BACK, HUH?
- THERE'S NOT ONE SANE PERSON
IN THE WHOLE PLACE.
- ERZA IS DUE BACK ANYTIME.
- UH...
- THE ERZA?
- YEP, SHE'S THE MOST
POWERFUL WOMAN
IN ALL OF FAIRY TAIL.
SHE'S SCARY LIKE A MONSTER.
THEY CAUGHT ME.
- GIVE HAPPY BACK!
- BUT WHAT COULD THIS MEAN?
- LULLABY...
- Man:
HEY, MIRA, CAN WE GET
THREE BEERS OVER HERE, PLEASE?
- BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
- SO WHEN ARE YOU AND I
GONNA GO ON A DATE, MIRA?
- WOULD YOU LEAVE HER ALONE?
- WAKABA, THERE'S ONE
SMALL PROBLEM.
YOU ALREADY HAVE A WIFE.
- I HATE IT WHEN YOU DO THAT!
IT'S SO CREEPY.
- I WISH I COULD DRINK
IN PEACE FOR ONCE.
- WELL, IF YOU DIDN'T DRINK
ALL DAY...
- I GUESS WE SHOULD PROBABLY
TRY TO FIND ANOTHER JOB.
- AYE, WE'RE RUNNING OUT
OF FOOD MONEY.
- IF WE'D TAKEN THAT
TWO MILLION JEWEL REWARD,
WE'D BE SITTIN' PRETTY.
AND I CAN'T LET MYSELF FORGET
THAT RENT'S GONNA BE DUE
NEXT WEEK.
I GUESS I'D BETTER
FIND WORK TOO.
- ( rock music plays )
- HMM...
FINDING A MAGIC BRACELET,
BREAKING A SPELL
ON A CURSED CANE?
READING SOMEONE'S
LOVE HOROSCOPE,
HUNTING A VOLCANO DEMON?
JEEZ, I HAD NO IDEA
WIZARDING JOBS WERE SO VARIED.
- WELL, LET ME KNOW IF
YOU FIND ONE
YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN TAKING ON.
THE MASTER'S AWAY
AT CONFERENCE,
SO I'M COVERING FOR HIM.
- WHAT KIND OF CONFERENCE?
- ONE FOR GUILD MASTERS.
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE,
THEY ALL GET TOGETHER
TO TALK ABOUT
THE STATE OF THINGS.
IT'S LIKE THE MAGIC COUNCIL,
BUT NOT.
EXCUSE ME, REEDUS?
COULD I BORROW A LIGHT PEN?
- OUI.
- Narrator:
A LIGHT PEN IS A MAGICAL ITEM
THAT ALLOWS THE USER
TO WRITE IN THE AIR.
- THE COUNCIL, ERA, IS
THE MOST POWERFUL ORGANIZATION
IN THE MAGICAL WORLD.
IT'S ONLY ONE STEP
BELOW THE GOVERNMENT.
IT HAS 10 MEMBERS,
AND IT'S THEIR JOB
TO UPHOLD ALL MAGICAL
RULES AND REGULATIONS.
AND IF A WIZARD BREAKS
MAGICAL LAW,
THEY WOULD BE TRIED
BY THE COUNCIL.
THEN THERE'S THE DIFFERENT
GUILD MASTER LEAGUES,
WHICH ARE LOCAL GROUPS
WHO WORK TOGETHER.
THEN THE INDIVIDUAL MASTERS.
IT'S THEIR JOB TO PASS ON
THE DECREES OF THE COUNCIL.
THEY ALSO COMMUNICATE
WITH OTHER GUILD MASTERS
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
THEY'RE THE GLUE
THAT HOLDS ALL OF US
TOGETHER.
WHICH IS A PRETTY
STRESSFUL JOB.
- WOW, I NEVER REALIZED THAT ALL
THE DIFFERENT MAGICAL GUILDS
WERE INTERCONNECTED
LIKE THAT.
- IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
WE COOPERATE WITH ONE ANOTHER,
OTHERWISE OUR SYSTEM
WOULD FALL APART.
- AND THEN THE GUYS IN BLACK
WOULD SHOW UP.
- AAH!
- ( laughs )
THAT WAS ALMOST TOO EASY! - YOU
TRYING TO SCARE ME TO DEATH?
- BUT SERIOUSLY, THE GUYS
NATSU'S TALKING ABOUT EXIST.
THEY'RE THE DARK GUILDS.
THEY'VE CHOSEN NOT TO JOIN
ANY OF THE LEAGUES.
THEY'RE THE BAD APPLES.
AND MOST OF THEM ARE INVOLVED
IN MAGICAL CRIME.
- WOW.
- WOULD YOU JUST GO
AND PICK US A JOB ALREADY?
- YOU HAVE GOT TO BE
KIDDING ME.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'D WANNA DO THAT?
- WELL, WE ARE A TEAM NOW,
AREN'T WE?
- YEAH, AND WE PICKED THE JOB
LAST TIME!
IT'S YOUR TURN TO PICK,
SO GET TO IT.
- JUST FORGET IT, CAT.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
OUR TEAM HAS BEEN DISBANDED.
AND BESIDES, YOU GUYS,
DIDN'T ACTUALLY WANT ME.
YOU JUST NEEDED ME LAST TIME
BECAUSE I'M A BLOND.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY REASON
WE CHOSE YOU.
WE PICKED YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE SO NICE.
- HEY, LUCY,
I WOULDN'T STAY
WITH THOSE LOSERS
IF I WERE YOU.
YOU'LL GET PLENTY OF OFFERS
FROM OTHER TEAMS.
- YOUR CLOTHES, GRAY.
- AAH!
- JERK!
- DID YOU JUST CALL ME A JERK,
DRAGON BOY?
- AND WHAT IF I DID?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
- YOU MOUTH-BREATHER!
- AT LEAST I'M NOT A COWARD.
- YOU'RE A SPINELESS WIMP!
- YOU'RE A FREAK!
- LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
AT IT AGAIN.
- WHY DON'T YOU JOIN
THE TEAM OF LOVE
WITH ME, LUCY?
LATER TONIGHT,
JUST THE TWO OF US?
- SAY WHAT?
- YOU'RE JUST
SO STUNNINGLY GORGEOUS.
I HAVE TO KEEP MY SHADES ON
WHEN I LOOK AT YOU.
OR I'LL BE BLINDED
BY YOUR DAZZLING BEAUTY.
- GIRLS REALLY FALL FOR THIS?
- YOU'RE NOT A CELESTIAL WIZARD,
ARE YOU?!
- HUH?
- YEAH, SHE'S GOT COWS
AND CRABS AND STUFF.
- AAH!
CURSE YOU, FATE!
WHY MUST YOU TOY
WITH ME SO?!
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU AND I
CAN'T BE TOGETHER, MY DEAR!
- WHAT GOT INTO HIM
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- LOKE HAS A BAD HISTORY
WITH CELESTIAL WIZARDS.
RUMOR HAS IT HE DATED ONE
AND IT DIDN'T END UP VERY WELL.
- WELL, I'M NOT SURPRISED--
- ( both scream, groan )
- THAT LOOKED PAINFUL.
- WOULD THE TWO OF YOU
JUST KNOCK IT OFF ALREADY?
- NATSU STARTED IT.
I'M JUST FOLLOWING THROUGH.
- WHERE ARE YOUR CLOTHES?
- AAH!
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
WAS PROVOKING ME.
YOU DIRTY SLIMEBALL.
- OH, YEAH?
AND WHAT EXACTLY DID I DO
TO PROVOKE YOU?
YOU FIRE CLOWN.
- YOU PERVY FLASHER!
- PINK-HAIRED PUNK.
- LAME INSULTS, GUYS.
- THEY START TO RUN OUT.
- IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?!
- PRETTY MUCH!
- ( all laughing )
- ( chuckles softly )
- I'VE GOT BAD NEWS!
- ( all gasp )
- IT'S ERZA--
SHE'S ON HER WAY HERE.
- ( all scream )
- WOW, JUST MENTION ERZA,
AND THE WHOLE PLACE FREAKS OUT.
- WELL, SHE IS THE
STRONGEST FEMALE WIZARD
WE'VE GOT IN FAIRY TAIL,
AND MORE THAN
A BIT INTIMIDATING.
- ( heavy footsteps
approaching )
- THAT'S GOTTA BE HER.
- THOSE SOUND LIKE
HER FOOTSTEPS.
- EVEN THE AIR'S GOTTEN
COMPLETELY STILL.
- JEEZ, FROM THESE REACTIONS,
YOU'D THINK SHE WAS
SOME KIND OF DEMON
OR SOMETHING.
- ( roars )
- ( screaming )
- I'M SO SCARED!
- I HAVE RETURNED.
WHERE IS MASTER MAKAROV?
- WOW, SHE'S PRETTY.
- WELCOME BACK, ERZA.
THE MASTER'S AT A CONFERENCE
RIGHT NOW.
- I SEE.
- SO, UM, WHAT'S THAT
HUMONGOUS THING YOU GOT THERE?
- IT'S THE HORN OF A MONSTER
THAT I DEFEATED.
THE LOCALS WERE SO THANKFUL,
THEY DECORATED IT
AND GAVE IT TO ME
AS A SOUVENIR.
DO YOU HAVE A PROBLEM WITH IT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL!
- I BET SHE'S HEARD ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED AT MOUNT HAKUBE.
- YOU THINK SO?
AW, MAN, I'M A GONER.
- SHE'S NOT ANYTHING
LIKE I IMAGINED.
- NOW, LISTEN UP.
- ( all gasp )
- WHILE I WAS ON THE ROAD,
I HEARD A FEW THINGS.
WORD IS FAIRY TAIL IS CAUSING
NOTHING BUT TROUBLE AS OF LATE.
MASTER MAKAROV MAY NOT CARE,
BUT I MOST CERTAINLY DO.
CANA, YOU NEED TO START
CONTROLLING YOUR DRINKING.
VIJEETER, PLEASE TAKE
THE DANCING OUTSIDE.
WAKABA, GET RID OF THAT
FILTHY HABIT.
NAB, I SUSPECTED I WOULD
FIND YOU DAWDLING
IN FRONT OF THE REQUEST BOARD.
JUST PICK A JOB!
MACAO...
( sighs )
- PLEASE JUST SAY SOMETHING!
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO BEGIN WITH YOU.
YOU CAUSE SO MUCH TROUBLE.
I'VE ALMOST GIVEN UP.
- SHE'S REALLY TEARING IN
TO EVERYONE.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S TAKING OVER.
- THAT'S ERZA FOR YA.
- EVEN IF SHE IS
KINDA BOSSY,
SHE'S STILL SANER THAN
ANYONE ELSE HERE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
EVERYONE'S SO AFRAID OF HER.
- ARE NATSU AND GRAY HERE?
- Happy: AYE!
- OH, HEY THERE, ERZA.
WE'RE JUST HANGING OUT
LIKE GOOD FRIENDS TEND TO DO.
- AYE! - WHY IS NATSU
TALKING LIKE HAPPY?!
- THAT'S GREAT. I'M QUITE
PLEASED TO SEE THE TWO OF YOU
GETTING ALONG SO WELL.
HOWEVER, IT'S ONLY NATURAL
FOR EVEN THE BEST OF FRIENDS
TO LOCK HORNS
EVERY NOW AND AGAIN.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
WE'RE THE BEST OF FRIENDS.
- AYE...
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO NATSU?!
- HE'S SCARED.
A FEW YEARS AGO,
HE CHALLENGED ERZA TO A FIGHT,
AND SHE BEAT HIM UP PRETTY BAD.
- THAT WAS A STUPID THING
TO DO.
- AFTER THAT, SHE FOUND GRAY
WALKING AROUND NAKED,
SO SHE DECIDED
TO BEAT HIM UP TOO.
- AND LET'S NOT FORGET,
SHE ALSO BEAT UP LOKE
FOR TRYING TO HIT ON HER.
- ( grunts )
- Cana: HE TOTALLY DESERVED IT,
THOUGH.
- Lucy:
YEAH, CAN'T SAY I BLAME HER.
- NATSU, GRAY...
I NEED YOU TO DO ME
A FAVOR.
WHILE TRAVELING, I OVERHEARD
SOMETHING THAT HAS ME WORRIED.
NORMALLY, I WOULD CONSULT
WITH THE MASTER BEFORE ACTING,
BUT HE'S NOT HERE AND THIS IS
A MATTER OF UTMOST URGENCY.
THE TWO OF YOU ARE
THE STRONGEST WIZARDS HERE.
I COULD REALLY USE
YOUR HELP.
- ( murmuring )
- DID THAT JUST HAPPEN?
- ERZA ASKED THEM FOR HELP?
- THIS IS DEFINITELY A FIRST.
- WE'LL MEET AT THE TRAIN
STATION TOMORROW MORNING.
- ME AND NATSU?
- ON THE SAME TEAM?
- ERZA, NATSU AND GRAY
WORKING TOGETHER?
I NEVER SAW THAT ONE COMING.
THIS COULD BE THE MOST POWERFUL
TEAM FAIRY TAIL'S EVER SEEN.
- ( exhales )
THEN?
- ( chattering )
- Narrator:
MAGNOLIA STATION.
- AAH!
I HATE THIS! TEAMING UP WITH
YOU WAS THE WORST IDEA EVER!
- YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
ERZA MADE A HUGE MISTAKE
ASKING A LOSER LIKE YOU
TO COME ALONG.
- FINE THEN, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TAKE CARE OF IT YOURSELF?
I DON'T WANNA GO ANYWAY.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN TO ME.
THEN I'LL GET TO WATCH HER
BEAT YOU SENSELESS.
- ( exhales )
- LET'S JUST SIT HERE
AND PRETEND
WE DON'T KNOW THEM.
- WHAT MADE YOU DECIDE
TO COME WITH US?
- MIRA ASKED ME
TO TAG ALONG.
- THOSE TWO ARE GONNA
BE AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS
WHEN ERZA'S NOT LOOKING,
SO I WANT YOU TO BE THERE
TO STOP THEM, OKAY?
- WHO, ME?!
- YOU AREN'T DOING
A VERY GOOD JOB.
- THEY'RE HOPELESS.
- ( indistinct muttering )
- Erza: SORRY I'M LATE.
HAVE YOU BEEN WAITING LONG?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
AAH.
WOW, LOOK AT THAT LUGGAGE!
ALL THOSE BELONG TO YOU?!
- IT'S TIME TO GO, GOOD BUDDY.
- AYE!  HA-HA!
- LISTEN, ONE HAPPY'S ENOUGH.
- GOOD, I REALLY LOVE TO SEE
THE TWO OF YOU GETTING ALONG.
AND WHAT WAS YOUR NAME?
I BELIEVE I SAW YOU
AT THE GUILD YESTERDAY.
- MY NAME'S LUCY,
AND I JUST JOINED FAIRY TAIL.
MIRA ASKED ME TO COME ALONG
WITH YOU GUYS
SO I COULD LEARN A THING OR TWO.
I HOPE THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
- THE MORE THE MERRIER.
I'M ERZA.
WAIT, YOU'RE THE GIRL
I HEARD ABOUT.
- ( lightly cheer )
- I WAS TOLD YOU DEFEATED
A MERCENARY GORILLA
USING ONLY YOUR PINKY FINGER.
- ( gasps ) - IT'LL BE GREAT TO
HAVE A WIZARD LIKE YOU ON BOARD.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- ( cheer )
- OH, NO, IT'S MY PLEASURE.
( chuckles nervously )
- HEY, ERZA, I'LL COME WITH YOU,
BUT ONLY UNDER ONE CONDITION.
- SHUT UP.
- OH?  WELL, THEN LET'S HEAR IT.
- 'KAY, I WANNA REMATCH
WHEN WE GET BACK TO FAIRY TAIL.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
GOT SOME KIND OF DEATH WISH?
- I'M A LOT STRONGER
THAN I WAS LAST TIME.
THIS TIME WILL BE
WAY DIFFERENT.
'CAUSE I'M GONNA BEAT YOU.
- YES, I CAN TELL
YOU'VE IMPROVED.
AS TO WHETHER OR NOT
YOU CAN BEAT ME,
I SUPPOSE WE'LL HAVE TO SEE.
I ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
- OH, YEAH!
I'M FIRED UP!
- ( train whistle blows )
- I SWEAR YOU'RE
TOTALLY PATHETIC, NATSU.
ONE MINUTE YOU'RE
PICKING A FIGHT,
THE NEXT, YOU'RE LIKE THIS.
- IT'S GOTTA BE TOUGH ON HIM,
GETTING FROM PLACE TO PLACE.
- DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL BE FINE.
COME HERE AND SIT WITH ME.
- I-- I GUESS SHE
WANTS ME TO MOVE.
- NOW JUST RELAX.
- ( groans )
AAH! - THERE. THAT SHOULD MAKE
THE TRIP A LITTLE EASIER ON HIM.
- OKAY, MAYBE SHE'S NOT AS SANE
AS I THOUGHT SHE WAS.
- ERZA, I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU STARTED FILLING US IN.
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF MISSION
ARE WE GOING ON HERE?
- OF COURSE.  I HAVE REASON
TO BELIEVE THE DARK GUILD
EISENWALD IS PLANNING
SOMETHING BIG.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT EXACTLY,
BUT IT HAS TO DO WITH
A MAGIC ITEM CALLED LULLABY.
- Both: LULLABY?
- WAIT, THAT THING FROM BEFORE?
- Narrator:
THE DARK GUILD, EISENWALD.
- Rayule: I HEAR KAGEYAMA
FINALLY GOT BACK TO US.
- Byard: YEAH, HE SAYS
HE ACTUALLY FOUND IT.
- THE MOMENT OF TRUTH
HAS ARRIVED, GENTLEMEN.
THIS MEANS WE'RE ONE STEP CLOSER
TO ACHIEVING OUR GOALS.
THE GUILD MASTERS WILL BE TOO
BUSY HOLDING THEIR CONFERENCE,
THEY WON'T EVEN REALIZE
WHAT'S HIT THEM.
- I SEE.  SO YOU'VE RUN INTO
THE EISENWALD GUILD BEFORE?
- WELL, I'M NOT POSITIVE
THEY WERE PART OF EISENWALD.
BUT THEY DID MENTION LULLABY.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
THEY WERE MEMBERS
WHO DROPPED OUT OF THE GUILD
AND GONE INTO HIDING.
PERHAPS THEY WANTED NO PART
OF WHATEVER IT IS
THAT'S COMING.
- SO THIS THING IS SO BAD
IT EVEN SCARES DARK WIZARDS?
- I'M ONLY HYPOTHESIZING.
BUT WHOEVER YOU SAW
DRAGGING OFF HAPPY'S KIDNAPPERS
THAT DAY, MUST HAVE BEEN
FROM EISENWALD.
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT THEY DIDN'T
WANT THEIR PLANS GETTING OUT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE GONNA TRY?
- LET ME START
FROM THE BEGINNING.
JUST THE OTHER DAY
I WAS HEADING HOME
AFTER COMPLETING A JOB.
I STOPPED BY A PUB
IN ONIBAS
THAT I KNEW WAS A GATHERING
SPOT FOR LOCAL WIZARDS.
- Byard: COME ON, HURRY IT UP,
BARTENDER!
- Rayule:
HEY, RELAX A LITTLE.
- AND HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT?
WE FINALLY MANAGED TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE LULLABY'S HIDDEN,
BUT WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
BECAUSE OF SOME SEAL?
- KEEP IT DOWN, MAN.
- DON'T SWEAT IT, YOU GUYS.
LET ME HANDLE THIS ONE.
YOU JUST HEAD BACK
TO THE GUILD, ALL RIGHT?
- YOU SURE, KAGE?
- YOU GONNA BE OKAY ON YOUR OWN?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ME.
JUST TELL ERIGOR THAT
I'LL BE COMING BACK
WITH LULLABY IN THREE DAYS.
- LULLABY?
THAT'S LIKE A SONG
YOU SING KIDS TO SLEEP.
- YES.  AND THE FACT
THAT IT HAD BEEN SEALED AWAY
MEANS THAT IT MUST BE
VERY POWERFUL MAGIC.
- YOU SURE THE GUYS YOU SAW
AT THE PUB ARE WITH EISENWALD?
- YES.  I CAN'T BELIEVE
I WAS SUCH A FOOL THAT DAY.
I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE HIS NAME.
ERIGOR, THE ACE OF EISENWALD.
HE ONLY ACCEPTS
ASSASSINATION REQUESTS,
WHICH IS WHY HE'S EARNED
THE NAME, "ERIGOR THE REAPER."
- Lucy:
HE KILLS FOR MONEY?
- WHEN THE COUNCIL OUTLAWED
ASSASSINATION REQUESTS,
EISENWALD DECIDED THAT MONEY
WAS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THE COUNCIL'S RULES.
AS A RESULT, THEY WERE KICKED
OUT OF THEIR WIZARD LEAGUE
SIX YEARS AGO.
BUT THAT DIDN'T STOP THEM.
THEY'VE DISOBEYED ORDERS
AND REMAINED ACTIVE TO THIS DAY.
- OKAY, I SHOULD BE
HEADING BACK HOME NOW.
- LUCY'S SLIMY ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- IT'S SWEAT!
- HOW COULD I HAVE BEEN
SO CARELESS?
IF ONLY I HAD RECOGNIZED
ERIGOR'S NAME THAT DAY...
I COULD HAVE
PULVERIZED THEM.
I COULD HAVE FORCED THEM
TO REVEAL THEIR SCHEME TO ME.
- SHE'S SCARY!
- SO IF I GOT THIS,
EISENWALD'S PLANNING TO DO
SOMETHING WITH THIS LULLABY,
AND YOU WANNA STOP THEM. BECAUSE
AFTER WHAT YOU OVERHEARD,
YOU'RE SURE THAT
IT'S GONNA BE SOMETHING BAD.
- THAT'S CORRECT.
AND I'M NOT FOOLISH ENOUGH
TO BELIEVE THAT I CAN TAKE ON
AN ENTIRE MAGICAL GUILD
ALL BY MYSELF.
THAT'S WHY I ASKED
YOU AND NATSU FOR YOUR HELP.
WE'RE STORMING
THE EISENWALD GUILD.
- SOUNDS LIKE FUN TO ME.
- AYE!
- I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME ALONG.
- EW, NOW YOU'RE SUPER SLIMY!
- I TOLD YOU, IT'S SWEAT!
CAN'T YOU GIVE ME A LITTLE
DISCOUNT, PRETTY PLEASE?
- ( blows )
- IF YOU DON'T MIND,
WHAT KIND OF MAGIC
DO YOU PRACTICE, ERZA?
- THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
- ERZA'S MAGIC IS REALLY PRETTY.
SHE MAKES HER ENEMIES
BLEED A LOT.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
I'D CALL THAT PRETTY.
- PERSONALLY,
I THINK GRAY'S MAGIC
IS MORE BEAUTIFUL THAN MINE.
- OH, LIKE THIS?
- ( rock music plays )
- I USE ICE MAGIC.
- Lucy: NOW I UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU AND NATSU DON'T GET ALONG.
HE'S FIRE AND YOU'RE ICE. TALK
ABOUT NOT MIXING VERY WELL.
- Erza:
I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT THAT.
- NAH, I JUST HATE HIS GUTS.
- Narrator:
ONIBAS STATION.
- Gray: YOU THINK
THE EISENWALD GUYS
ARE STILL GONNA BE IN THIS TOWN?
- Erza:
I HAVE NO IDEA.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE HERE
TO FIND OUT.
- I'M STILL THINKING
MAYBE I SHOULD GO HOME.
- HOLD ON, WHERE'S NATSU?
- ( groaning )
- ( Lucy screams )
- UH-OH, THERE HE GOES.
- WE WERE SO BUSY TALKING,
I FORGOT ABOUT HIM.
I AM SUCH A FOOL. NATSU HATES
ALL FORMS OF TRANSPORTATION.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT. I NEED
ONE OF YOU TO COME AND HIT ME
FOR MY PENANCE.
- THAT'S A LITTLE MUCH.
- ( groans)
- WELL, LOOK IT HERE.
IT'S A FAIRY TAIL WIZARD.
HOW'S THE GUILD TREATING
YOU THESE DAYS?
IS IT WORTH STICKING AROUND?
- WHAT?
- DON'T ACT
ALL HIGH AND MIGHTY
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE IN
A LEGAL GUILD, MR. FAIRY.
YOU GUYS WHO JUST BLINDLY
FOLLOW THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
KNOW WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE TO US?
HARMLESS LITTLE FLIES.
( laughs )
GUESS I HIT A NERVE.
- YOU-- ( groans )
- ( laughs )
WHAT KIND OF MAGIC IS THAT?
LET ME SHOW YOU
HOW IT'S DONE.
IT'S ALL IN THE FOLLOW-THROUGH.
- THAT MAGIC...
- ( chuckles )
- ( brakes screech )
- ( both grunt )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING, LADY? YOU CAN'T PULL
THE EMERGENCY LEVER
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
- IT'S FOR OUR COMRADE.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- NOW I WOULD LIKE YOU TO
TAKE OUR LUGGAGE
TO THE HOTEL.
- DO I LOOK LIKE A BELLHOP?
- I'M STARTING TO REALIZE
THAT ALL OF THE WIZARDS
IN THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD
ARE JUST A LITTLE INSANE.
- Happy: WOW...
- WELL, NOT ALL OF US.
- OH, YEAH, WHERE ARE
YOUR CLOTHES?!
- THE TRAIN STOPPED.
WHAT IS THAT?
- ( groans )
YOU SAW IT.
- THAT'S ENOUGH OUT OF YOU.
IT'S PAYBACK TIME.
( grunting )
- GUARD SHADOW!
- ( explosion )
- LUCKY SHOT.
- HMM.  LITTLE FLY, HUH?
- Woman on P.A.:
ATTENTION, ALL PASSENGERS,
OUR EMERGENCY STOP
WAS A FALSE ALARM.
WE'LL BE DEPARTING AGAIN
SHORTLY.
- OH, CRAP, I GOTTA GO.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
I'M NOT LETTING YOU
GET AWAY THAT EASILY.
YOU'RE MESSING WITH
EISENWALD NOW.
- OH, SO YOU'RE WITH
EISENWALD, HUH?
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT HAPPENS
TO PEOPLE WHO KNOCK FAIRY TAIL.
HOW 'BOUT WE TAKE THIS OUTSIDE?
- ( rumbling )
- Both: WHOA...
- ( gags )
- Narrator:
THIS IS A MAGIC-MOBILE.
IT'S A FAST VEHICLE THAT RUNS
ON THE DRIVER'S MAGIC ENERGY.
- Lucy:
NATSU!
- ( screams )
- ( all grunt, scream )
- NATSU, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- UH...
- Happy: ( in pain ) AYE!
- THAT HURT, YOU IDIOT!
- SHUT UP, YOU ICY FREAK.
HOW COME YOU GUYS LEFT
ME ON THE TRAIN?
- I'M JUST THANKFUL YOU
WEREN'T BADLY INJURED.
I APOLOGIZE, NATSU.
- HUH!  IT'S OKAY.
WELL, I'M SHAKEN UP
PRETTY BAD.
I GOT ATTACKED BY
A WEIRDO ON THE TRAIN.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- I THINK IT'S THE DUDE THAT
DRAGGED AWAY THE GUYS
WHO WERE GONNA EAT HAPPY.
SAID HE WAS WITH EISENWALD.
AAH!
- YOU FOOL!
THAT IS EXACTLY WHO WE'RE
CHASING AFTER ON THIS MISSION.
WHY DID YOU LET HIM GET AWAY?!
- WHAT THE-- THIS IS
THE FIRST I HEARD ABOUT IT.
- I EXPLAINED EVERYTHING
ON THE TRAIN.
YOU SHOULD LISTEN
WHEN PEOPLE TALK TO YOU.
- SHE ALREADY FORGOT THAT
SHE KNOCKED HIM OUT, DIDN'T SHE?
THIS WOMAN IS UNBELIEVABLE.
- YEP.
- THAT'S ERZA FOR YA.
- SO HE WAS ON THE SAME TRAIN
THAT WE WERE ON.
LET'S FIND HIM.
- BUT WHAT WAS THIS GUY LIKE?
- HE DIDN'T LOOK LIKE SOMEBODY
FROM A DARK GUILD.
BUT HE DID HAVE THIS STRANGE
FLUTE THING.
IT LOOKED LIKE A SKULL,
EXCEPT IT HAD THREE EYES.
- Lucy:
THE THREE-EYED SKULL?
- Gray:
THAT'S CREEPY.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG,
LUCY?
- IT'S JUST, I'VE HEARD
ABOUT THAT FLUTE BEFORE.
LULLABY...
THE CURSED SONG.
IT'S DEATH MAGIC.
- WHAT? - A CURSED SONG?
LIKE AN INCANTATION?
- I'VE ONLY EVER READ ABOUT THEM
IN BOOKS BEFORE,
BUT THERE'S SOME DEADLY SPELLS
OUT THERE
THAT ARE FORBIDDEN
TO BE USED BY WIZARDS.
- THAT'S RIGHT, THERE ARE
CURSED BLACK MAGIC SPELLS
THAT WILL KILL THE PERSON
THEY'RE USED ON.
- WELL, IF I'M RIGHT,
LULLABY IS EVEN WORSE.
- ( screaming )
- THIS TRAIN BELONGS
TO EISENWALD NOW.
- Narrator:
KUNUGI STATION.
- GET EVERYTHING
OFF THE TRAIN--
LUGGAGE, THE CONDUCTOR,
ALL OF IT.
IF ANYONE TRIES TO DEFY US,
KILL THEM ALL.
- WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- KAGEYAMA.
I HEARD YOU WERE COMING BACK
ABOARD THIS TRAIN.
THAT'S QUITE A BIT OF WRECKAGE.
CARE TO EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENED?
- COME ON, AREN'T YOU
INTERESTED TO SEE
WHAT I BROUGHT BACK WITH ME?
HA-HA, I FINALLY MANAGED TO
BREAK THE SEAL. - EXCELLENT.
- OH, YEAH.
- IS THAT IT?
- YES, THIS IS IT, MEN.
THE FORBIDDEN LULLABY.
ORIGINALLY, IT WAS A TOOL
FOR CASTING SIMPLE DEATH CURSES.
USEFUL, BUT LIMITED.
THAT IS UNTIL THE GREAT
BLACK WIZARD ZEREF
TRANSFORMED IT
INTO A DEMON FLUTE.
NOW ITS SONG
WILL KILL HUNDREDS,
THOUSANDS AT ONCE,
LULLING THEM ALL INTO
ENDLESS SLEEP.
AND IT'S ALL MINE.
- HEY, SLOW DOWN, ERZA.
YOU'RE USING TOO MUCH OF YOUR
POWER DRIVING THIS THING.
- I HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO PRESS ONWARD.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
IF ERIGOR GETS HIS HANDS
ON THIS DEATH MAGIC,
TRUST ME,
LIVES WILL BE LOST.
CURSE THEM.
WHAT IS IT THEY HOPE
TO ACCOMPLISH?
THIS IS MADNESS.
- ( laughing )
AND SO IT BEGINS.
LET'S MOVE FORWARD, MEN.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( shouts )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, MIRA, DO YOU THINK
ERZA'S SCARY?
- OH, NO, I DON'T
THINK THAT AT ALL.
I THINK SHE'S SWEET.
- ( sighs )
THANK GOODNESS.
THAT'S SUCH A RELIEF TO HEAR.
- BUT IF YOU MAKE HER MAD,
SHE MIGHT SEND YOU
FLYING WITH A PUNCH.
OR BURY YOU UP TO
YOUR NECK IN DIRT,
WHICH MIGHT BE UNCOMFORTABLE.
- OH, MY GOSH!
I DON'T WANT ANY OF
THAT STUFF TO HAPPEN TO ME!
- ( Mira and Lucy speaking )
- Mira:
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY,
SHE JUST TAKES SOME
GETTING USED TO, YOU KNOW?
( chuckles ) SHE USED TO GET MAD
AT GRAY AND NATSU ALL THE TIME.
- OH, I'M SURE SHE'LL GET MAD
AT ME BEFORE TOO LONG.