Is Lucy doing all right?
Yeah, she seems fine. Says
she wants to take a shower.
I can go and check on
her again if you want.
[ELFMAN] No way!
Are you crazy?
You can't do that now!
But why not?
[ERZA] Don't
even think about it.
The second match
is about to begin.
Yeah, this is prob'ly
more exciting anyway.
♪
[CHAPATI] It's only day
one of the Grand Magic
Games and this second
match in the battle round
already has us on
the edge of our seats!
[CHAPATI] It's Blue
Pegasus' Ren Akatsuki
versus Mermaid
Heel's Araña Web!
Will the playboy get tangled up?
[HAPPY] Portent!
You're stronger
than last year
but you're still
not gonna beat me.
I thought a Pegasus
man would
object to attacking a lady.
I guess I was wrong.
These two are tough!
Just look at that determination.
This should
be a great match!
Go Ren!
Win this one for Blue Pegasus!
Sherry's in the stands
and she's rooting for you!
Hey!
[ARAÑA] You left
yourself wide open!
You've gotta
pay attention, Ren!
Now go out there
and kick her butt!
What do you
think you're doin'?
The last thing we need is one of
our own rootin' for the enemy!
Geez, Give the kid a break,
old hag; they are
engaged after all.
Shut yer trap!
Want me to spin ya?
[LAMIA SCALE WIZARD 160A]
You already are!
What the hell're
you talking about?
We are not engaged!
I just can't get rid of her.
Get it straight!
[SHERRY] You're so mean!
[REN] You're always
stuck to my side.
Gah, it's annoying!
That said,
whenever you're not
around I just don't
feel like myself.
Told ya they were an item!
That's so sweet of you.
Why do chicks
always seem to
fall for the bad-boy jerk types?
[TOBY] I dunno.
Oh, don't be jealous.
As long as
she's watching I
can't go makin'
a fool of myself.
I refuse!
[REN] Aerial Forze!
Way to go, baby!
[CHAPATI] And the winner is
Ren Akatski of Blue Pegasus!
Their guild has
scored an impressive
fourteen points on day one.
While Mermaid Heel
only has three points!
Que cosa.
Shouldn't have let
my guard down.
Yay!
I knew you could do it, Ren!
[ERZA] Wow, his
skills have improved
immensely over the
last seven years.
You don't
think that this
guy's stronger
than Ichiya, do you?
[ERZA] Natsu
don't be ridiculous.
[ERZA] Ichiya is an
extraordinary man.
He may be a little strange but
he is, without a doubt,
the most powerful wizard
in Blue Pegasus.
Whoa.
I really had no idea.
Ichiya's that strong?
Now all I can think about
is squaring off with him.
I can't help
but be suspicious
of whomever is hiding
in that rabbit suit.
So you think
that's weird, too?
Well, that's good to know.
I didn't wanna be
rude, but ever since
I first saw him I've
been crackin' up.
[CHAPATI] It's time for the
third match of day one!
Quatro Cerberus' Warcry.
[CHAPATI] Versus
Sabertooth's Olga Nanagia!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160A] Yes!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160B]
He's so awesome!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160C]
Slaughter 'im!
Just listen to the crowd!
He's incredibly popular!
You're ready for this;
I know you can do it, Warcry!
Show this dude what it means
to be one of the Wild Bunch!
Check it out,
it's Warcry!
This'll be good.
Have you seen his magic before?
It's pretty entertaining.
[RUFUS]
Yes, I find it fascinating.
In fact I've memorized it.
[ROGUE] I couldn't care less.
[ROGUE THINKS] The only wizard
who interests me is you Gajeel.
I'm curious to see how
Sabertooth does
in a one on one battle.
Well, if their guy
is as strong as he looks,
this fight is gonna
be over super quick.
So tell me Lector,
who do
you think's gonna
win this match?
I think we both know
that Olga's got it in the bag!
Oh.
He must've rigged
the fight, huh?
Look, Sting is the
best wizard we've
got but all our
members are really strong.
Geez Frosch, if you
don't know that much,
you must be even dumber
than I thought you were.
I might be
dumb but I'm cute!
[CHAPATI]
Match three begins now!
There he goes!
That's Warcry's
signature tear magic!
Can't say I've
ever heard of it
but the name sure is fitting.
He's bawlin'!
Yes, he certainly is.
That is so not manly.
With my magic, the
more tears that I shed...
[WARCRY] ...the
stronger that I become!
Let's go!
[crowd cheers]
Lightning, huh?
[LECTOR AND FROSCH] Yeah!
He used lightning.
It took one blow!
[CHAPATI] And the third match
is over in a literal flash!
Olga's black lightning scorched
Warcry's tears for the win!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160D] No way!
It's already over?
[MALE SPECTATOR 160E]
Whoa, Olga beat him that quick?
[MALE SPECTATOR 160F]
Yeah, that guy's a monster!
[CHAPATI] And with
that one-hit K.O.,
the winner is Sabertooth's
Olga Nanagia!
[CHAPATI] His team has
dominated today's events!
They've scored a
total of twenty points!
[CHAPATI] Meanwhile,
Quatro Cerberus
only has two points!
What a cryin' shame!
[STING]
What's the rush, Olga?
Couldn't you have made
it a little more entertaining?
[OLGA] Alright fine,
I'll go sing a song.
[STING] That ain't what
I meant, ya big meathead!
[OLGA] Gimme the mic!
[CHAPATI] I dunno
what's going on out there
but it looks as though Olga's
about to make a speech!
[OLGA] You other guilds
think that you're cool,
but we're so strong we're
gonna make you drool!
There ain't no stoppin' the
Sabertooth guild, you losers
can try but you're
gonna get killed!
[OLGA] There ain't no doubt
about it, we're number one!
we're always on the
lookout, for a little fun!
you get in our way, then
you're gonna go down!
[MAVIS] That Sabertooth
worries me.
I hate to say it.
But I'm not sure that we'll
be able to beat them.
[ROMEO] Yeah, it sucks to admit,
but they're awesome.
[CHAPATI] Day one's
matches are about to come
to a close, but we still
have one more battle!
[YAJIMA] Fairy Tail B
and Lamia Scale must be
competing since they're the
only teams we haven't seen yet.
[JENNY] These two guilds
used to be equally-skilled
so this should be
an interesting fight.
I can't wait to see which
team comes out on top!
[CHAPATI] Okay folks,
are you ready?
The final match of the
first day is going to be.
Fairy Tail B's Mystogan versus
Lamia Scale's Jura Nekis!
[crowd erupts in cheers]
[MALE SPECTATOR 160G]
I can't wait!
[BOY SPECTATOR 160A]
Way to go, Jura!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160H] Hooray!
He's the only reason I
came to watch the games!
[FEMALE SPECTATOR 160A]
I never would've expected
him to fight on
the very first day!
[ERZA THINKS] Jellal,
right off the bat?
And he's fighting against
Jura, of all people!
[CHAPATI] Mystogan is such
a mysterious wizard that
only a select few in Fairy Tail
have ever seen his face!
[FEMALE SPECTATOR 160B]
You gotta be kiddin' me!
[FEMALE SPECTATOR 160C]
That's ridiculous!
[SHELIA] Good luck
out there, Jura!
[YUKA] This match
is as good as ours.
[TOBY] It ain't even
started yet, Yuka!
[YUKA] Chill out, man.
There's no need
to get ticked off.
[crowd cheers]
[BOY SPECTATOR 160B]
Look! It's Jura!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160I]
He's the coolest!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160J] Oh wow!
It's really him!
[MALE SPECTATOR 160K]
This is gonna be great!
Wow, I had no idea that
Jura guy was so popular!
Yeah, of course he is.
I mean, he is one of the
Ten Wizard Saints, after all.
He's basically as strong
as Master Makarov.
[LAXUS] I guess luck
isn't on your side today.
Who'd have thought you'd
be forced to fight Jura?
He's just a big,
bald priest.
Is he really that tough?
I'm not even sure
that Erza and I
could beat him in
a two-on-one battle.
[JELLAL] Don't worry.
You can count on me.
[JURA] Personally, I would
love to see Fairy Tail do
well in this competition,
but I'm afraid the old
hag would throw a fit
if I were to let you win.
My sincere apologies
but I won't be holding back.
[JELLAL] Nor will I.
[JELLAL] It was
never my goal to
enter into the arena
as a competitor.
But nothing makes me
happier than being given
the chance to fight for
my friends in Fairy Tail.
There's no need to
look so glum, First Master.
He'll be just fine.
You know, he once held
the very same title
as Iron Rock Jura.
So I think it's fair to say
that they're evenly matched.
[MAKAROV] Something wrong?
Sorry.
I was listening but I really
need to go to the restroom.
[ALL] For real?
But you're a ghost!
[ERZA THINKS] Jellal.
I hope you're
going to be all right.
What?
Jellal is fighting in
the next match?
Ya think he'll
be found out?
No, he's too smart
to let that happen.
That is, unless he
tries to show off
for Erza, then he
could ruin everything.
[CHAPATI] Fairy Tail B's
man of mystery going
head to head with
Lamia Scale's iron rock!
[CHAPATI] So let's get
this final match underway.
Right now!
[JELLAL] I might not
get another chance
to help Fairy Tail in the games.
[JELLAL] I've got to make the
most of it, and defeat Jura!
Whoa, that was
totally awesome!
[JELLAL]
Five-Layer Magic Circle.
Sacred Song!
That's nuts.
I can't believe he's
copying Mystogan's magic.
Very impressive.
Oh no, Jura!
Don't you
worry about him...
I don't mean to belittle
Juvia's team, but I happen to
think that Jura is the
greatest wizard in all of Fiore.
[JELLAL]
Three-Layer Magic Circle.
Mirror Water!
He deflected it!
Hell yeah, he did!
It's headed back to him!
[CHAPATI]
It's obvious why Jura's
one of the Ten Wizard Saints!
Because he rocks!
Yes, that's
the spirit, Jura!
Now hurry and finish him off!
Don't make me spin you!
[LAMIA SCALE WIZARD 160A]
Hey, cut it out, old hag!
[JELLAL] I should've
known I wouldn't be
able to beat him using
someone else's magic.
[JELLAL] Meteor!
But that's...!
No way!
[JURA] Iron Rock Wall!
There you are!
[JELLAL] Perfect timing.
There are magic
circles in the sky!
But how'd
they get there?
He must've drawn them
while dodging Jura's attacks!
[JELLAL] May the seven stars
bring judgment upon you!
Grand Chariot!
Rock Tor!
[JURA THINKS]
Just as I suspected.
I know exactly who you are now.
Unfortunately, it seems
my candid advice
to Fairy Tail's master
fell on deaf ears.
[JURA] By the way,
Sir Makarov, the Wizard
Saints will be holding
a meeting very soon.
You should come.
You need to be
debriefed and there's
a matter of importance
to discuss.
[JURA THINKS] I've been wary
of you and your guild
for some time Jellal,
but I never expected you to
assume the role of
a Fairy Tail wizard.
[JURA] Perhaps I should
have acted on my intuition.
[JELLAL] I have to win this
match, for Fairy Tail's sake.
[JELLAL] Forgive me, Ultear.
but I'm going to use it now!
Just what do you
think you're doing, Jellal?
This is bad!
If he uses that spell,
he's gonna blow his cover!
[JELLAL] True Heavenly
Body Magic: Sema!
What has he done?
[ULTEAR] How could
he be so stupid?
You see, that's the
problem with men!
They can't control
their ridiculous egos!
[MELDY] What are
we gonna do now?
[Ultear chuckles]
[JELLAL] The inside of my mouth!
[JELLAL] It's on fire!
Here ya go, why don't you
have some more hot peppers?
Eat!
[MELDY] No, it hurts!
They're too spicy!
Don't be a wuss!
C'mon, down the hatch!
[CHAPATI] I don't know what
happened, ladies and gentlemen,
but all of a sudden Mystogan
is writhing in agony!
Now let's see how
you like this, Jellal!
[MELDY] Please stop tickling me!
I can't take it!
[Jellal laughs]
[CHAPATI] If there's a joke
here, I am not in on it!
[ULTEAR] Oh, it's not over yet.
[ULTEAR] How do you like this?
[ULTEAR] And what about that?
[MELDY] Cut it out!
I can't take it anymore!
[CHAPATI]
Down in a fit of laughter!
[CHAPATI] I dunno
what was so funny,
but it put Mystogan
outta commission!
Sorry about that.
But we couldn't afford to let
Jellal attract too
much attention.
[CHAPATI] Jura Nekis gets
the last laugh and the win!
You done good!
You sure about
that, old hag?
Well folks,
that's a wrap for
day one of the
Grand Magic Games!
Let's see how the teams are
sizing up on the scoreboard!
[JET] What?
Team A has zero points
and Team B only has one?
This is a disaster.
Didn't I tell you
guys that we never
should've entered
in the first place?
It's been an exciting
day, hasn't it?
The talent level this
year is off the charts.
As we expected, the Sabertooth
guild is in first place...
...while the two Fairy Tail
teams are in dead last.
Yes but remember
it's only the first day.
Here's hoping
that we'll see some
dramatic comebacks
in the days ahead.
[JENNY] Yeah, Blue Pegasus
still has a chance to win!
I can't wait to see what's
in store for day two!
[CHAPATI] I'd like to thank you
for joining me today,
Mr. Yajima and Ms. Jenny!
[YAJIMA] It was my pleasure.
[JENNY] I had fun!
See you tomorrow!
[crowd laughing]
[MALE SPECTATOR 160L]
What a loser!
[MALE SPECTATOR]
Is he, like, Fairy Tail's
jester or somethin'?
[FEMALE SPECTATOR 160D]
That was hilarious!
Oh, good grief.
I don't understand; what
the heck happened to him?
I assume it was
Meldy's doing.
Way to make our team
look like a bunch of idiots!
[MIRAJANE] You tried your best.
[LAXUS] Man, you're pathetic.
[JELLAL] I'm sorry
that I let you guys down.
Oh, hey Lucy!
[ERZA] Feeling better?
Much better, thanks.
Our team's in last place.
[LEVY] "The first day of
the Grand Magic Games
was a disappointment."
"The Fairy Tail guild
couldn't have gotten
off to a worse start."
[LEVY] "Little did we
know there was something
terrible going on
behind the scenes."
It's finally bearing fruit.
[LEVY]
"I'm writing to you now that
the Grand Magic Games are over.
They ended a few days ago."
[LEVY] "To my dear
friend Lucy Heartfilia.
From Levy McGarden."
[CARLA] What was that?
Some kind of premonition?
Nothin' to worry
about, Lucy!
I'm gonna be competin' tomorrow!
[NATSU] And I'm gonna
turn things around for us!
You'll see!
♪
[HAPPY] I can't believe you're
in last place with zero points.
[NATSU] Do I look worried?
We're about to get
back in the game,
'cause I'm competing
in the next contest!
[HAPPY] Chariots, huh?
I wonder what kind of
game that's gonna be.
[NATSU] It doesn't matter!
I'm gonna win!
[HAPPY] That annoying Saber guy
and Gajeel are gonna
be competing, too!
[NATSU] It doesn't matter!
I'm gonna win!
[HAPPY] Good!
You'd better!
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next time: Chariots!
[HAPPY] Chariot's another
word for a battle wagon, right?
Aw, man.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[NATSU] Off I go!
Wish me luck!