- Gray: PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY
TAIL"... - Happy: GRAY TOLD US
SOMEONE NAMED DAPHNE
SAID SHE'D MET A DRAGON.
SO WE WENT TO THE
RISE LODGE TO SEE
IF WE COULD FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
- Carla: I SENSED SOMETHING WAS
OFF, AND OF COURSE I WAS RIGHT.
NOW I'M TRAPPED
WITH THIS MORONIC TOMCAT.
- Daphne: YES YES YES, I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU, DRAGON SLAYERS.
- Natsu: WAIT A MINUTE. WHAT THE
HECK IS GRAY DOING HERE?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Wendy: HE LOOKS MAD!
- Happy: PLEASE LET THIS
BE A BAD DREAM.
- GET BEHIND ME.
JUST DO IT.
HE'S NOT JOKING AROUND.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS, GRAY?
IS IT 'CAUSE
YOU HAVE A TUMMY ACHE?
- DON'T BE SUCH AN IDIOT!
- PLEASE DON'T FIGHT.
- STAY OUT OF OUR WAY.
ICE MAKE LANCE!
- HE ATTACKED HIM
USING HIS FULL STRENGTH.
- STAY CLOSE TO ME,
UNDERSTAND?
- YOU TWO HAVE ALWAYS
BUTTED HEADS,
BUT THERE'S NO NEED FOR THIS.
- HA HA HA!
MY MY.  YOU JUST DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
START FIGHTING BACK OR YOU'LL
END UP SKEWERED OR A POPSICLE.
NOW, GRAY FULLBUSTER,
GO GET ME A DRAGON SLAYER!
- YOU'LL GET ONE SOON ENOUGH.
- THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU
AT ALL, GRAY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS BY NOW?
WHAT I WANNA KNOW IS WHY
YOU'RE STANDING THERE
DOING NOTHING ABOUT IT.
- YOU THINK THIS GRAY
IS A FAKE?
- I SUPPOSE IT'S POSSIBLE.
WE HAVE SEEN MAGIC
LIKE THAT BEFORE,
BUT I'M NOT SURE--
- NO, WENDY'S RIGHT.
THIS ONE'S DEFINITELY DIFFERENT
THAN THE GRAY WE KNOW AND LOVE.
- HOW IS HE DIFFERENT?
HE SEEMS IDENTICAL.
- WELL, FOR STARTERS--
AH!
- IF YOU KEEP DODGING,
THIS'LL GET BORING.
COME ON!
- HE TOOK HIS CLOTHES OFF!
THIS GUY IS THE REAL GRAY
AFTER ALL.
- Both: ARE YOU KIDDING?
- ( Happy speaking )
- IF IT'S A REAL FIGHT YOU WANT,
YOU KNOW I'M DOWN.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I WAS STARTIN' TO GET BORED.
ICE MAKE BATTLE AXE!
- FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- YES YES,
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
THERE'S NOTHING QUITE LIKE
DINNER AND A GOOD SHOW.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THAT'S NO CHEAP
IMITATION PUNCHING YOU.
THAT'S THE GENUINE GRAY.
I PROMISE I'M NOT
CONTROLLING HIS MIND
OR ANYTHING CLICHE LIKE THAT.
HE'S BEATING YOUR FACE IN
SIMPLY BECAUSE HE WANTS TO.
- I DON'T NEED YOU
TO FIGURE THAT ONE OUT.
I'VE FELT
THAT IRRITATING PUNCH PLENTY.
NO FAKE GRAY COULD EVER HOPE
TO PULL IT OFF.
- YA KNOW, I HAD A FEELING
YOU WERE LETTING ME HIT YOU
SO YOU COULD TEST ME,
OR SOMETHING STUPID LIKE THAT.
- FIRE DRAGON TALON!
WE'RE JUST GETTING STARTED.
- YOU CAN WIN THIS!
- THOSE TWO
ARE SUCH BARBARIANS.
- IT'S TIME FOR SOME ANSWERS.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING HERE.
AT THE VERY LEAST YOU OWE ME
THAT MUCH.
- A CITY WITHOUT SOUND.
- WHAT WAS THAT? YOU'RE NOT
MAKING ANY SENSE, MAN.
WOULD YOU SPEAK PLAINLY?
- THAT'S AS PLAIN
AS YOU'RE GONNA GET.
WHATEVER, I DOUBT
YOU'D UNDERSTAND IT ANYWAY.
GET READY TO TAKE
YOUR LAST BREATH.
- THE TWO OF THEM HAVE REALLY
STEPPED UP THEIR GAME LATELY.
- THIS IS NOT THE TIME
FOR SLACK-JAWED GAWKING.
- AYE. - I DON'T GET
WHY THIS IS HAPPENING.
WHY WOULD GRAY BETRAY
HIS FRIENDS LIKE THIS?
- NOT THAT IT'S
ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT THAT HANDSOME SLAB
OF ICE
OFFERED TO HELP ME ON A SPECIAL
PROJECT. - WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I FIRST ARRIVED
IN MAGNOLIA ABOUT 10 DAYS AGO
TO CONTINUE MY RESEARCH.
I WAS DOING SOME DIGGING
INTO NATSU DRAGNEEL'S
BACKGROUND, WHEN I--
( swallows ) --WHEN I RAN
INTO GRAY FULLBUSTER.
HE SHOWED INTEREST
IN MY PROJECT
AND WAS VERY WILLING TO LEND
HIS HAND TOWARDS COMPLETING IT.
SO HE LURED
THE SALAMANDER HERE FOR ME.
HE'S QUITE THE CATCH,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- COLD-BLOODED BETRAYAL,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
- NO WAY.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT.
- I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
GOING ON BETWEEN YOU TWO.
YOU AND GRAY...
ARE GETTING
ALL LOVEY-DOVEY!
- MAYBE.
- HOW SCANDALOUS!
WHEN JUVIA FINDS OUT
ABOUT THIS,
SHE'S GONNA MORE VICIOUS
THAN ALL OF
THE ORACION SEIS COMBINED!
- COULD YOU BE
ANY MORE OBNOXIOUS?
SHUT UP, GET OVER HERE, AND I
DON'T WANT TO HEAR ANOTHER PEEP.
- I'M SORRY, CARLA.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- OKAY, SO YOU AND GRAY
ARE PARTNERS NOW,
BUT WHAT IS THIS
CITY WITHOUT SOUND?
AND WHAT'S YOUR INTEREST
IN NATSU?
I DON'T UNDERSTA--
- YES YES,
YOUR QUESTIONS CAN WAIT.
FOR NOW, HOW ABOUT SAMPLIN'
ONE OF METAMO-CHAN'S FLAVORS?
- WHO COULD POSSIBLY EAT
THAT TRIPE AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
- OH YEAH, GIVE ME ONE
OF THE FISHY FLAVORED KIND.
- DO YOU HAVE A SINGLE SHRED
OF SELF-CONTROL?
- MMMM!  AHHH!
- Daphne: GOT A KICK, DON'T IT?
YOU WANT A NIBBLE?
- Wendy: WHO IS THIS LADY?
- COME ON!
I'M ALL FIRED UP NOW.
BEEN AWHILE SINCE MY BLOOD
WAS BOILING OVER LIKE THIS.
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL ME
WHAT'S GOIN' ON,
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO BEAT IT
OUT OF YOU.
AHHH!
- Erza: THEY'RE LATE.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
BE HOLDING THEM UP?
IT DOESN'T TAKE THIS LONG
TO FOLLOW A SIMPLE LEAD.
- HE WAS ASKING SOMEONE
ABOUT THE DRAGON SIGHTING.
YOU THINK HE FOUND
WHAT HE WAS LOOKING FOR?
- MAYBE NATSU'S PLAYING CATCH-UP
WITH IGNEEL RIGHT NOW.
- OR HE GOT TIRED
OF CHASING RUMORS, GOT FED UP,
AND CALLED IT A NIGHT.
- NO.
NORMALLY I'D AGREE,
BUT NATSU HAD WENDY WITH HIM.
HE WOULD'VE
BROUGHT HER BACK FIRST.
- SALAMANDER MIGHT BE RECKLESS,
BUT HE WOULDN'T KEEP A KID
OUT THIS LATE AT NIGHT.
THAT'S JUST
NOT THE KIND OF MAN HE IS.
- WHAT'S MORE,
WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT BECAME OF MY ATTACKER
FROM EARLIER THIS AFTERNOON.
HE COULD'VE
AMBUSHED THEM TOO.
- I'M AFRAID THAT GRAY
IS OUT THERE NEEDING MY HELP.
WE SHOULD FORM A SEARCH PARTY
IMMEDIATELY.
IF SOMETHING'S
HAPPENED TO HIM,
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE MYSELF
FOR NOT BEING THERE.
- GRAY'S A BIG BOY.
HE CAN TAKE CARE OF HIMSELF.
- SERIOUSLY,
YOU WORRY WAY TOO MUCH.
IT'S BAD FOR YOUR HEALTH.
- YOU'D BE WISE
NOT TO UNDERESTIMATE
THE INTUITION OF A WOMAN
MADLY IN LOVE.
- SHE'S DEFINITELY GOT THE MAD
PART DOWN TO A "T."
- AT LEAST WE'RE NOT DROWNING
IN HER TEARS.
- I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR THEM.
LUCY, YOU'RE WITH ME.
- JUST LEAD THE WAY.
- I WILL ACCOMPANY YOU AS WELL.
- YOU'RE GONNA NEED A
MAN WITH YOU. - NO.
WE CAN'T DIVIDE OUR FORCES
SO THINLY.
REMAIN ON STANDBY
AND GUARD THE HALL.
- WE'LL DO OUR PART.
CAREFUL OUT THERE, YOU TWO.
- YOU WON'T GET PAST MY--
ICE MAKE SHIELD!
- FIRE DRAGON TALON!
- ICE MAKE FLOOR!
- AHH!
- GEEZ, YOU'RE PATHETIC.
- YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
YOU TRAITOR!
FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
- DON'T HURT EACH OTHER.
- THIS FIGHT COULD LAST
TILL THE END OF EXISTENCE.
- Carla: DON'T BE SO DRAMATIC.
AT THE RATE THEY'RE GOING,
THEY'LL WEAR THEMSELVES OUT.
- Happy: YOU CAN DO IT, NATSU!
- FIRE DRAGON FLAME ELBOW!
- IT'S A POOL.
- GRAY JUST GOT
THE FIELD ADVANTAGE.
- YOU'RE GOING DOWN NOW.
GOOD LUCK DODGING THIS.
ICE MAKE PRISON!
- OH, THIS IS SO
NOT PLAYING FAIR!
LET ME OUTTA HERE AND FIGHT
LIKE A MAN.
COME ON, IT'S COLD.
- YES YES YES.
NOT ONLY IS HE GOOD LOOKING,
BUT IT APPEARS
HE'S QUITE
THE BRILLIANT TACTICIAN.
I KNEW PARTNERING WITH HIM
WAS A SMART MOVE.
- YOU BELONG IN A CAGE, HA.
- I'M NOT SOME WILD BEAST, JERK!
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
DARN IT,
I CAN'T SEE A THING.
- YOU FELL FOR IT, MORON.
- SON OF A--
- ICE MAKE LANCE!
I THINK WE BOTH KNEW DEEP DOWN
THAT THIS
WAS GONNA HAPPEN SOMEDAY.
FIRE AND ICE JUST DON'T MIX.
- IF THAT'S HOW YOU REALLY FEEL,
THEN I'M NOT HOLDING BACK
ANYMORE.
- TIME TO SAY GOODBYE.
- I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
GOODBYE!
- NATSU! - Carla: THEY'RE
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
LET'S HURRY.
- Wendy: OKAY.
NATSU!
YOU OKAY?
I KNOW YOU WON'T AGREE,
BUT THE ONLY WAY WE CAN STOP 'EM
IS WITH MY SKY DRAGON MAGIC.
- NO, CHILD.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO HELP,
BUT USING YOUR MAGIC
IN THESE TIGHT QUARTERS
COULD SERIOUSLY INJURE SOMEONE.
- FINE.
I'M FLYING BACK TO TOWN
FOR REINFORCEMENTS.
BE BACK!
- WAIT, DON'T TOUCH THE--
- YOUR STUPIDITY IS PAINFUL
TO WITNESS.
- YES YES, THERE'S NO ESCAPING.
IT'S POINTLESS TO RESIST,
SO WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TO RELAX FOR A WHILE?
- THE ONLY WAY OUTTA HERE
IS TO BEAT HER UP!
- WHILE YOU WAIT,
PLEASE ENJOY SOME
OF THE LEAFY GREEN VARIETY.
- GROSS!
- LIKE I SAID,
ESCAPE IS IMPOSSIBLE.
THIS LODGE IS MY ILLUSION,
SO IF I WANT YOU TO
STAY, YOU STAY.
- THIS LODGE ISN'T EVEN REAL?
- YES YES,
I USE CONCEALMENT MAGIC
THAT HIDES ANYONE AND ANYTHING
FOR AS LONG AS I WANT.
AND THIS QUAINT LITTLE BUILDING
WAS CREATED
USING MY HIDDEN CAGE SPELL.
IT MAY NOT LOOK LIKE MUCH,
BUT IT FOOLED YOU, RIGHT?
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
YOU WON'T HAVE TO CALL
FOR REINFORCEMENTS.
- THEY CAME LOOKING FOR US.
HEY, WE'RE UP HERE!
- HURRY,
NATSU NEEDS YOUR HELP!
- THAT INN SHOULD BE
RIGHT AROUND HERE.
DO YOU THINK WE MISHEARD
THE DIRECTIONS?
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
STAY SHARP.
IT'S THE SAME SMELL
AS BEFORE.
- ERZA, WHAT IS THAT THING?
- THAT'S WHAT ATTACKED ME.
I HAD A FEELING
IT'D SHOW UP AGAIN.
- LUCY, I WANT YOU
TO STAY BEHIND ME.
- YOU GOT IT.
- TELL ME WHAT
YOU'RE PLANNING HERE!
ARE YOU THE REASON NATSU AND
THE OTHERS HAVEN'T COME HOME?
ANSWER ME!
- ERZA!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
OPEN!
GATE OF THE MAIDEN!  VIRGO!
- ( bell dings )
- IS THERE SOMEONE YOU'D LIKE ME
TO SPANK FOR YOU, PRINCESS?
- WE GOTTA WORK
ON YOUR TURN OF PHRASE.
- I LOOK FORWARD
TO BEING DISCIPLINED.
- WHATEVER.
ERZA NEEDS OUR HELP, PRONTO.
- IT WOULD BE MY PLEASURE.
PRINCESS,
WE DON'T APPEAR TO BE ALONE.
- I DIDN'T THINK
THERE'D BE MORE THAN ONE.
- HAVE NO FEAR, PRINCESS.
I WILL TAKE CARE OF THIS ONE.
- SHE'S GONNA TRY TO CATCH IT
OFF GUARD.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA, VIRGO.
IS THAT THING USING
THE SAME ABILITY?
- DID HE FLEE?
THE WAY YOU DIG
LACKS ANY DISCIPLINE
OR REFINED FORM OF GRACE.
REVEAL YOURSELF NOW.
I WILL HAPPILY INSTRUCT YOU
IN THE PROPER FORM.
IT APPEARS AS THOUGH HE CAN
INCREASE HIS STRENGTH OVER TIME.
SPICA LOCK!
SORRY, PRINCESS.
I FAILED.
- YOU DID GREAT, VIRGO.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A BREATHER?
- I'LL SERVE YOU
BETTER NEXT TIME.
- NOW YOU ASKED FOR IT.
- ( bell dings )
- IT'S BEEN AWHILE.
'SUP, GORGEOUS?
- I'M KIND OF
IN A BIND RIGHT NOW,
BUT I KNOW
YOU CAN HELP ME OUT.
- I NEVER TURN MY BACK
ON A BEAUTIFUL FACE.
THAT'S NOT HOW THE LEADER OF
THE ZODIAC SPIRITS DOES THINGS.
I STILL OWE YOU ONE FOR TAKING
IN ARIES AND THE OTHERS.
ALWAYS HOPED
THEY'D WIND UP WITH YOU.
- NO, IT CHANGED AGAIN.
- ALL RIGHT, SO HE'LL BE
A TOUGH NUT TO CRACK.
IT'S NICE TO HAVE CHALLENGES.
CUTE TRICK!
IF YOU WANNA CHALLENGE
A CELESTIAL SPIRIT
TO A BARE-KNUCKLED BRAWL,
FINE BY ME.
WHAT THE--
HE GOT WAY STRONGER.
- I JUST FIGURED OUT
WHAT IT'S DOING.
- IMITATION MAY BE FLATTERY,
BUT WHAT YOU'RE
DOING HAS NO STYLE.
- ERZA!  LUCY!
- SAVE YOUR BREATH, CHILD,
I DOUBT THEY CAN HEAR US
WHILE WE'RE INSIDE.
- LET ME GUESS.
THOSE LIZARD HEADS
ARE WORKING FOR YOU?
- WHAT A SMART KITTY CAT.
AND THEY'RE
NOT THE ONLY ONES EITHER.
I'VE GOT A MENAGERIE OF
ARTIFICIAL PLAYTHINGS
IN MY ARSENAL.
- YOU MEAN
THEY'RE NOT REALLY ALIVE?
- THEY MUST BE GOLEMS THEN.
- BINGO.
AND THOSE BAD BOYS
WILL TAG TEAM WITH A GOLEM
THAT MATCHES THE ABILITIES OF
THE OPPONENT THEY'RE FIGHTING.
MAGNOLIA HAS THE BEST WIZARDS
AROUND,
SO I'M TAKING THE OPPORTUNITY
TO GATHER DATA ON THEM
WHILE GRAY DEALS
WITH THE SALAMANDER.
- WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING TO DO
WITH THAT DATA?
- NOW THAT, KITTY CAT,
IS THE BIG QUESTION.
BE PATIENT, THE REAL SHOW
WILL START SOON.
WHY SPOIL THE SURPRISE WHEN I
CAN UNVEIL IT IN GRAND FASHION?
- ( crashing )
- MY MY.
THOSE BOYS LIKE TO PLAY ROUGH,
DON'T THEY?
- GOTTA SAY, OF ALL THE TIMES
WE'VE FOUGHT,
THIS ONE'S THE BEST BY FAR.
- YEAH, SOMEHOW YOU'VE ALWAYS
FOUND A WAY TO KEEP UP WITH ME.
- COME ON NATSU, GIVE HIM
ONE RIGHT IN THE FACE!
- YES YES, SPLENDID.
EVERYTHING'S GONE
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
ALL RIGHT, GRAY FULLBUSTER.
TIME TO FINISH
THIS LITTLE GAME!
- IT'LL BE MY PLEASURE.
NATSU!
- YOU LOSE!
- YES, NATSU WON!
- HE CERTAINLY LIVES UP TO
HIS REPUTATION. - WHOA.
- HA HA.
IMPRESSIVE, DRAGON BOY.
- HA HA!
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GLAD WE GOT THAT SETTLED.
HUH?  GRAY?
WHAT?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
I DIDN'T THINK
I'D KNOCKED YOU OUT COLD.
NO PUN INTENDED.
HOLD ON A SEC. I DIDN'T
DO MORE THAN THAT, DID I?
AH!
MY TOES ARE GOING NUMB.
- IDIOT.
YOU'LL NEVER LEARN,
WILL YOU?
- YES YES YES!
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
HIDDEN DARKNESS!
- AHHH!
- YES YES,
YOU'VE PERFORMED BRILLIANTLY.
SEEMS YOU'RE WORTHY OF BEING
MY PARTNER. - 'PRECIATE IT.
TOOK A BIT MORE WORK
THAN I EXPECTED.
- Happy: NO!
- Wendy: WHAT DO WE DO?
- YOU TRICKED US.
IT WAS NEVER YOUR INTENTION
TO HARM HIM.
YOU WERE LURING HIM
INTO THIS SETUP. - YEP.
HE'S STRONG,
BUT I ALSO USE MY BRAINS.
- YOU ARE SUCH A LIAR.
YOU JUST WON
BECAUSE YOU CHEATED.
- YOU CAN JOIN HIM
IF YOU WANT, FUR BALL.
- STOP!
LET GO!
- YES YES.
QUIT FOOLING AROUND,
YOU IMBECILE.
IT TOOK THIS MUCH EFFORT
JUST TO GET THE IMPORTANT PART
OF MY EXPERIMENT IN PLACE.
- I GUESS
I'M NOT THE IMPORTANT PART?
- SO TRAPPING NATSU
WAS YOUR GOAL FROM THE START?
- YES.  MY RESEARCH
IS FINALLY COMPLETE.
NOW THE FUN BEGINS.
- HAPPY!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WENDY, YOU THERE?
TESTING, ONE, TWO, THREE!
- Young Natsu:
WHOA, A DRAGON EGG!
- ( squawking )
- I BET IGNEEL'S OVER THERE.
IGNEEL!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
DON'T LEAVE.
I WANNA COME WITH YOU!
IGNEEL, PLEASE WAIT.
DON'T GO!
IGNEEL.
Natsu: IGNEEL.
I REMEMBER THAT EGG.
AND THE CITY WAS DEAD QUIET.
WAIT A MINUTE.
A CITY WITHOUT SOUND.
AHHH!
- NATSU?
- All: AHH!
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THE SOUND
OF MY LITTLE SURPRISE.
- Erza: I UNDERSTAND.
THEY SWITCH OUT
WITH ONE OF THEIR KIND
THAT HAS THE SAME ATTRIBUTES
AS THEIR OPPONENT.
AND THAT'S WHERE
THEIR WEAKNESS LIES.
REQUIP!
ADAMANTINE ARMOR!
YOU NEED TO WORK
ON YOUR TIMING.
YOU'VE GOT QUITE A COLLECTION.
BUT THE FACT THAT YOU
CAN MATCH MY ARMOR
DOESN'T HELP YOU AT ALL.
THERE'S NO ONE IN THIS WORLD
WHO CAN REQUIP AS FAST AS ME.
NEXT TIME USE YOUR OWN STRENGTH
TO FIGHT YOUR BATTLES.
- THIS IMITATION CRAP
IS GETTING ON MY NERVES.
BUT I THINK WE CAN USE IT
TO TAKE THIS GUY DOWN.
- YEAH, AND I KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT TO DO.
- WELL,
IT'S BEEN FUN REGARDLESS.
TAKE CARE, BEAUTIFUL.
- OPEN!
GATE OF THE LITTLE DOG--
NICOLA!
- ( carnival music playing )
- ( squeals )
- YES!
JUST AS I PLANNED.
YOU CAN DO IT.
- ( both panting )
- ( weakly ) HOORAY!
- YOU'VE GOTTEN STRONGER.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, PLUE.
- AHH.
- HA HA HA.
- YES YES, IT'S ALIVE!
CONCEALMENT MAGIC, DISPERSED.
PREPARE TO ACTIVATE
LACRIMA CORE!
UNLOCKING
ALL JOINT RESTRICTORS.
NEUROTRANSMITTER LACRIMA
CONNECTION IS GOOD TO GO.
ANYTHING LIVING
THAT'S NOT SALAMANDER,
GET AWAY
FROM MY PRECIOUS BABY!
YES YES YES.
FIRING UP THIS BAD BOY
WITH A SALAMANDER HEART.
LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED!
- AHHH!
- NOW MY DRAGONOID, ACTIVATE!
- INTERESTING NAME CHOICE.
- I DON'T THINK
WE WANNA KNOW
WHAT SALAMANDER HEART
REALLY MEANS.
- AHHH!
- Lucy: NATSU!
SO LOUD!
- YES YES YES.
LIKE A NEWBORN, IT CRIES!
SUCH MAJESTY!
THE WORLD'S FIRST ARTIFICIALLY
CONSTRUCTED DRAGON!
THE UNSTOPPABLE DRAGONOID.
AND NOW SALAMANDER'S MAGIC
POWER IS ITS LIFE BLOOD.
- IT'S USING HIS MAGIC POWER?
- LUCY AND ERZA!
YOU'RE OKAY!
- I'M GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
- WE WERE SO WORRIED.
- WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING
FAST.
- FIRST YOU NEED
TO TELL US WHAT'S GOING ON.
- WHERE'S NATSU?
- HE'S INSIDE THAT BIG DRAGON.
THIS CRAZY LADY NAMED DAPHNE
SET A TRAP FOR HIM,
AND GRAY LURED HIM INTO IT.
- Both: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- WHAT'S WORSE
IS HE'S NOT BEING MANIPULATED.
IT'S ALL ON PURPOSE.
GRAY'S DOING ALL OF THIS
OF HIS OWN FREE WILL.
- UP THERE.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: HAPPY, DID I JUST
GET EATEN BY A DRAGON?
- NO, GOOFBALL,
IT'S A DRAGONOID.
DAPHNE BUILT IT,
LIKE A GIANT TOY.
- WHAT?
SO IT'S A FAKE?
AWWW, AND HERE I WAS ALL
PUMPED UP FOR A MANO-A-MANO,
BALLS-TO-THE-WALL,
DRAGON-SLAYER FIGHT!
TALK ABOUT A BUZZ KILL.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
GET YOURSELF CAPTURED, GENIUS.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu: WHAT?
I DIDN'T GET CAUGHT.
I, UH,
I'M RIDING THIS THING.
- Happy: WAIT, IF THAT'S THE
CASE, SHOULDN'T YOU BE VOMITING?
- ( Natsu grumbling )