- WITH THE 88 HEAVENLY BODIES.
SHINING!
URANOMETRIA!
( screaming )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( water splashing )
- ( gasping )
DID I JUST WIN?
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
HIBIKI!
HAPPY!
NATSU,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( panting )
- I WILL NOT LOSE!
- ( computerized beeping )
- I'M ONE OF THE ORACION SEIS.
YOU NEVER STOOD A CHANCE.
- ( Happy speaking )
- Lucy: WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT FEELS LIKE
ALL MY STRENGTH WAS DRAINED.
AND WHY DOES SHE LOOK LIKE SHE
FOUGHT A TORNADO HEAD ON?
- I'LL USE
THE LAST OF MY POWER
TO SEND YOU TO THE GRAVE!
NO.
YOU MISSED!
FILTHY TRAITOR.
- ( beeping )
- ( shivering )
- HANG ON!
- Angel: WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I PRAYED FOR?
WHAT I WANTED
MORE THAN ANYTHING...
WAS TO VANISH,
INTO THE HEAVENS,
LIKE AN ANGEL,
PURE AND WHITE.
BUT I KEEP ENDING UP
ALL WET!
- IT'S MOVING TOO FAST.
- ( mumbling )
- YOU'VE GOTTA
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
COME ON, I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
TAKE MY HAND!
GOT YA!
- Both: OH!
- Lucy: AHH! WHERE DID
THESE RAPIDS COME FROM?
OH, NO WAY.
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
NATSU!
- ( bell dings )
- THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
ANGEL HAS ALSO
BEEN DEFEATED?
MARK MY WORDS,
I SHALL AVENGE YOU ALL.
SOON THE LIGHT OF THIS WORLD
WILL COME CRASHING DOWN.
- I'M STILL ALIVE,
YOU KNOW.
- Erza: JELLAL.
HE'S COME BACK.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
AND WHY DID HE SHOW UP HERE,
OF ALL PLACES?
- Young Jellal:
LET'S GO, OKAY?
- Jellal: THERE IS NO HEAVEN,
NOR DOES TRUE FREEDOM
REALLY EXIST.
- Young Jellal:
SHE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
- I WISH I KNEW WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE
FEELING RIGHT NOW.
- Jura: HOLD ON.
SO WHAT YOU'RE TELLING ME
IS THAT NIRVANA'S MAGIC
ACTUALLY ALTERS THE
PERSONALITIES
OF THOSE IT AFFECTS?
- PRECISELY RIGHT.
OH YEAH.
WITHIN ITS AREA OF EFFECT,
THAT BLACK LIGHT
WILL FORCIBLY CHANGE
ANYONE WHOSE HEART
IS TEETERING ON THE EDGE
OF GOOD AND EVIL
TO THE OPPOSITE OF THEIR
USUAL NATURE. OH YEAH.
- IF WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS TRUE,
THAT WOULD MEAN
YOU WERE WAVERING BETWEEN LIGHT
AND DARKNESS YOURSELF.
- I WAS NEVER TRULY EVIL
TO BEGIN WITH.
AND I COULD NO LONGER
CONVINCE MYSELF
WHAT I WAS DOING WAS NOBLE.
OH YEAH.
- I DON'T SEE HOW YOU COULD
EVER JUSTIFY WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
- WHEN YOU'VE LOST A LOVED ONE,
YOU CAN JUSTIFY ANYTHING,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
MY ONLY GOAL WAS TO FIND
MY LONG-LOST BROTHER.
TO DO THAT, I NEEDED HEAPS
AND HEAPS OF MONEY.
OH YEAH.
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU,
ALL OF MY PRECIOUS MEMORIES
CAME CRASHING TO THE SURFACE.
- LET ME GUESS--
I BEAR A STRIKING RESEMBLANCE
TO THIS LONG LOST BROTHER
OF YOURS?
- HMM HMM! QUITE HONESTLY,
YOU LOOK LIKE A POTATO
MY BROTHER AND I
ONCE SPLIT TOGETHER.
- DON'T TELL ME THAT!
- ONWARD.
LET'S STOP BRAIN AND HIS
MINIONS TOGETHER, FOR LOVE!
OH YEAH!
- UM, SURE.
- HAVING TROUBLE?
- IT'S LIKE MY MAGIC
HAS NO EFFECT ON YOU.
BUT I HAVE TO KEEP TRYING.
AIR MAGIC, AERIAL SHOT!
YOU'RE GOIN' DOWN!
YOU'VE GOTTA
BE KIDDING ME!
AHH!
NO.
WHY COULDN'T I HIT YOU?
- HMM.  TWO DOWN.
THESE GUYS ARE SO PITIFUL.
COME ON.
THIS IS THE BEST THEY'VE GOT?
- MAYBE I SHOULDN'T
HAVE JOINED THE ALLIANCE.
- CHILD,
STOP BEATING YOURSELF UP.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
- YES, IT WAS.
- YOU'RE PLAYING
WITH FIRE, WENDY.
NIRVANA COULD CHANGE YOUR HEART
AT ANY MOMENT.
- I'M A COWARD.
I LEFT LUCY
AND THE OTHERS
INSTEAD OF STAYING
TO FIGHT WITH THEM.
- YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
THAT IF YOU HAD STAYED,
YOU WOULD ONLY BE IN THE WAY.
- Wendy: SEE?
I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
- DON'T YOU DARE SAY THAT.
REMEMBER, IF YOU HADN'T BEEN
HERE, THEY WOULD'VE LOST ERZA.
- YEAH.
BUT THE ORACION SEIS
FOUND NIRVANA BECAUSE OF ME.
- IS IT REALLY ALL THAT BAD,
CHILD?
I SENSE PART OF YOU IS GLAD
TO SEE THAT JELLAL FELLOW AGAIN,
THOUGH I'M NOT SURE WHY.
- ( sighs )
- AND WHILE
WE'RE ON THAT SUBJECT,
WOULD YOU CARE TO EXPLAIN
WHO HE IS?
YOU SAID SOMETHING ABOUT OWING
HIM YOUR LIFE. BUT I'M CONFUSED.
IF HE'S SO IMPORTANT, WHY HAVE
YOU NEVER TOLD ME ABOUT HIM?
- IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
IT JUST NEVER CAME UP.
I MET HIM SEVEN YEARS AGO
NOT LONG AFTER SKY DRAGON
GRANDINA DISAPPEARED.
HE FOUND ME SCARED, ALONE,
AND WANDERING AIMLESSLY.
- GRANDINA!
WHERE'D YOU GO?
PLEASE, COME BACK.
( sobbing )
- WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
- SHE LEFT ME.
( crying )
SHE LEFT ME ALL ALONE!
- Wendy:
THAT'S HOW WE MET.
HE SAID HE WAS ON HIS OWN TOO
AND HE ASKED IF I WANTED
TO JOIN HIM ON HIS JOURNEY.
WE TRAVELED TOGETHER
FROM THAT DAY FORWARD.
WE DIDN'T KNOW
WHERE WE WERE GOING,
BUT I DON'T THINK
WE REALLY CARED.
- YOU CAME BACK!
- I NORMALLY
DON'T LIKE RAINY DAYS,
BUT FOR SOME REASON THIS DOESN'T
BOTHER ME AT ALL. HUNGRY?
- WOW!  HOW WERE YOU ABLE
TO FIND SO MUCH FOOD?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU READY TO CHOW DOWN?
- MM-HMM!
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
- THAT'S WAY BETTER.
- WHICH WAY
DO YA THINK WE SHOULD GO?
- I DON'T KNOW. THERE'S TONS
OF PLACES WE COULD GO.
- I'M FINE GOING ANYWHERE
AS LONG AS IT'S WITH YOU.
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- ( giggles )
- Wendy: THEN ONE DAY,
HE STARTED ACTING STRANGE.
- ANIMA!
- WHAT?
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
BUT WHY--
I WANNA STAY WITH YOU.
- YOU CAN'T.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS, ALL RIGHT?
- DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
I'LL FIX IT.
PLEASE, JELLAL,
DON'T LEAVE ME.
- THERE'S A GUILD ACROSS THE
FOREST WHERE YOU'LL BE SAFE.
WE'LL STOP THERE, BUT THEN
WE'LL HAVE TO PART WAYS.
- NO!
- WENDY, COME ON.
- Wendy:
WHEN WE GOT BEYOND THE FOREST,
HE LEFT ME
WITH THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD.
I'VE BEEN THERE EVER SINCE.
- SO WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM
AFTER YOU PARTED WAYS?
- THAT WAS THE LAST TIME
I EVER SAW HIM.
BUT I DID HEAR RUMORS
NOW AND THEN.
FIRST PEOPLE SAID THERE WAS A
COUNCIL MEMBER
WHO LOOKED LIKE HIM.
AND THE MOST RECENT ONES
WERE ALL ABOUT
HOW HE WAS DOING
THESE INCREDIBLY EVIL DEEDS.
SO SILLY.
HE'D NEVER THINK ABOUT
DOING SUCH HORRIBLE THINGS.
I WONDER--
DO YOU THINK HE REMEMBERS ME
ANYMORE?
- Cobra: NO.
SHE SURVIVED?  IMPOSSIBLE.
WHY WASN'T I ABLE
TO SENSE HER APPROACHING?
I CAN'T LET HER
TAKE JELLAL DOWN
BEFORE NIRVANA
IS FULLY ACTIVATED.
- JELLAL.
- ERZA.
- NOW TELL ME,
HOW DID YOU END UP HERE?
- I CAN'T ANSWER THAT.
ERZA.
WHO IS THAT?
I HAVE NO MEMORY.
AND YET I REMEMBER THAT NAME.
I DON'T KNOW WHO I AM
OR WHERE I CAME FROM.
CAN YOU TELL ME?
DO YOU KNOW?
AT LEAST TELL ME
WHO ERZA IS.
PLEASE, IF YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
HIS MEMORY'S
BEEN WIPED CLEAN?
- OH, JELLAL.
- AHHH!  WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, GRAY?!
DON'T YOU WORRY CARLA,
MY LOVE.
YOU JUST HURRY
AND GET WENDY TO SAFETY
AND LET THE CATMANDER
TAKE CARE OF SAVING HIS BUDDY!
HUH?
THERE'S NOT EVEN ANYBODY AROUND!
AND I WAS SOUNDING
TOTALLY MACHO TOO.
- Jellal: PLEASE, IF YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
- Cobra: YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
HIS MEMORY'S BEEN WIPED CLEAN?
- JELLAL.
- STAY BACK!
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN YOU COME TO ME.
I'M THE PERSON
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
I AM ERZA.
AND YOU ARE JELLAL.
THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN WE WERE CLOSE FRIENDS.
- WE WERE?
- YES, BUT THAT WAS BEFORE
YOU BECAME DERANGED,
DESECRATED THE DEAD,
HURT MY FRIENDS,
DESTROYED THE MAGIC COUNCIL
AND KILLED SIMON.
IF YOU TRY--
IF YOU EVEN DARE FORGET
THE PAIN YOU'VE CAUSED,
I'LL TAKE MY SWORD TO YOUR HEART
AND ENGRAVE IT THERE!
NOW COME TO ME.
FACE YOUR ATONEMENT!
- I DID THAT TO MY COMRADES?
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
PLEASE, NO.
TELL ME IT'S NOT TRUE.
TELL ME.
HOW CAN I MAKE AMENDS?
- IS THIS THE SAME JELLAL?
- WHO DID THIS?
QUESTION TWO--
WHO CHANGED MY CLOTHES?
- I THOUGHT GARMENTS FROM THE
CELESTIAL WORLD WOULD SUIT YOU.
AS FOR WHO CHANGED YOU,
THAT WOULD BE ME.
- VIRGO?
- ( grunts )
OKAY, NOW WHERE AM I?
- I ALSO PROVIDED SIR NATSU
WITH A MATCHING SET.
- TOTALLY NOT NECESSARY.
- I'M WASTING TIME HERE.
WHERE'S THAT WEIRD
LIGHT THINGY?
- Lucy: WELL, WE'RE CLOSER, BUT
IT LOOKS DIFFERENT THAN BEFORE.
- Virgo: YES, THE LIGHT
CHANGED FROM BLACK TO WHITE
WHILE THE TWO OF YOU
WERE UNCONSCIOUS.
- ( exhaling )
- ( gasps )
- THANKS A LOT FOR SAVING MY
BUTT BACK THERE, LUCY.
- UH, YEAH, SURE,
DON'T MENTION IT.
- SHE LOVES YOU.
- DON'T COPY
THAT STUPID CAT AGAIN!
- SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WHERE IS HAPPY?
- I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
- NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT,
WASN'T A CERTAIN BLONDE
SUPPOSED TO STAY WITH ERZA?
- I WAS,
BUT WE GOT SPLIT UP.
- THEN WHY ARE WE
STANDING AROUND WASTING TIME
WHEN WE SHOULD BE RUNNING
TOWARD THE LIGHT?
- I'M HAPPY I COULD SERVE YOU,
PRINCESS.
UNTIL NEXT TIME.
- WAIT!
THAT'S RIGHT,
I DIDN'T SUMMON HER.
SHE MUST HAVE CROSSED OVER
USING HER OWN POWER.
DOES THAT MEAN I USED UP
ALL OF MINE?
AHH!
SHERRY!
- ( Sherry moans )
- I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALL RIGHT,
BUT DID YOU HAVE SCARE ME?
- HEY, I KNOW YOU.
WEREN'T YOU
ON BIG TUNA ISLAND?
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO THAT DOG
AND THE DUDE WITH THE EYEBROWS?
- GALUNA ISLAND,
AND YOU'VE SEEN HER SINCE THEN.
- IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
YOU FAIRY TAIL MEMBERS
ARE TO BLAME.
- EXCUSE ME?
- ( laughs )
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU!
- ( gasping )
- IS SHE OKAY?
- I THINK SHE MIGHT
BE POSSESSED.
- GET OFF OF ME! YOU'LL PAY FOR
WHAT YOU DID TO MY LOVE.
YOU'LL NEVER
LEAVE THIS FOREST.
- SHE'S BEEN ACTING STRANGE
SINCE THAT LIGHT SHOWED UP.
HAVE YOU SEEN ANYTHING WEIRD?
- YEAH, AND I OWE YOU
A KICK IN THE TEETH
FOR THAT LITTLE TRICK
YOU PULLED. - HUH?
- NATSU, THAT WASN'T REALLY GRAY
BACK THERE.
- YOU WON'T ESCAPE ME.
I SWEAR ON MY LIFE
I'LL AVENGE HIM.
- AVENGE ME FOR WHAT, EXACTLY?
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT YOU HAD
MORE FAITH IN ME THAN THAT.
- IS IT REALLY YOU?
- OF COURSE, HE'S A WHOLE
LOT TOUGHER THAN HE LOOKS.
- Lyon: IT WAS CLOSER
THAN I'D CARE TO ADMIT.
EVEN AFTER I PUT SOME DISTANCE
BETWEEN US AND THE BOMB,
I SPENT EVERYTHING I HAD
KEEPING THE BLAST AT BAY.
IT TOOK ME A WHILE
TO RECOVER.
- Lucy: SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAD
AS ROUGH A TIME AS WE DID.
- WOW, NATSU,
WHERE'D YOU FIND THAT GET-UP?
- WHY, YOU JEALOUS?
- I SERIOUSLY DOUBT
THAT'S THE CASE.
- OH, MY LOVE.
- WHOA, WHAT'S THAT?
- I TOLD YOU GUYS SHE SEEMED
LIKE SHE WAS POSSESSED.
- NO KIDDING.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
- IT APPEARS THAT THE BLACK
HAS VANISHED FROM THE PILLAR.
- I WONDER IF THAT'S A GOOD
OR A BAD SIGN.
- PLEASE!
WAKE UP!
HIBIKI!
WE'VE GOT TO HELP THE OTHERS.
BE SAFE, YOU GUYS.
I SWEAR I'LL BE THERE SOON.
NATSU, ERZA.
- Cobra:
IF YOU'VE LOST YOUR MEMORY,
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN WHY
I COULDN'T HEAR YOUR THOUGHTS.
BUT NOW I'VE GOT A WHOLE SLEW
OF QUESTIONS FOR YOU TO ANSWER.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
WE WERE BEING WATCHED.
- I'D LIKE TO KNOW
HOW YOU FOUND NIRVANA.
BUT EVEN MORE THAN THAT,
I WANNA KNOW
HOW YOU BROKE ITS SEAL.
- WHILE I WAS UNCONSCIOUS,
I HEARD A VOICE.
"I MUST HAVE NIRVANA",
IT WOULD SAY.
IT'S STRANGE,
BUT WHEN I WOKE UP,
I KNEW PRECISELY
WHERE TO FIND IT.
SOMEHOW I COULD ALSO SENSE
HOW INCREDIBLY DANGEROUS
AND POWERFUL IT IS.
AND SO I DECIDED
TO BREAK NIRVANA'S SEAL,
TO OBLITERATE IT.
- HOW DO YOU INTEND
TO DESTROY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- I'VE RIGGED THIS MONSTROSITY
WITH A SELF-DESTRUCTION CIRCLE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE NIRVANA CRUSHES ITSELF.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN A MAGIC CIRCLE
WITH THIS KIND OF COMPLEXITY.
IF I CAN'T FIND A WAY
TO STOP THIS,
WE'LL LOSE EVERYTHING.
SPILL IT, JELLAL!
TELL ME HOW TO DISARM IT
OR I'LL BEAT IT OUT OF YOU.
- ( grunts )
ERZA.
WHENEVER I HEAR THAT NAME,
A CALMNESS WASHES OVER ME.
( coughing )
CHEERFULNESS,
KINDNESS,
FIERCE UNWAVERING LOYALTY.
I HAVE NO DOUBT
YOU'LL CONTINUE TO DESPISE ME.
BELIEVE ME,
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
I WOULD PROBABLY FEEL
THE SAME.
IF I AM TRULY YOUR FRIEND,
THEN I CAN'T ALLOW
THAT HATRED
TO KEEP ROBBING YOU
OF YOUR FREEDOM. ( grunts )
- BUT WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- ( sighs )
I'M SORRY YOU'VE SUFFERED
BECAUSE OF ME.
I'LL DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO MAKE IT RIGHT.
- YOU DIDN'T.
- BE FREE, ERZA,
FROM YOUR HATRED.
ESCAPE YOUR PAST.
I WILL TAKE YOUR PAIN
AND YOUR SADNESS--
ALL OF IT.
THEY CANNOT SHACKLE YOU.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S GONNA GO THROUGH WITH IT.
HE'S SERIOUSLY
GONNA SACRIFICE HIMSELF.
- FAREWELL, ERZA.
- Erza: JELLAL!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: OH NO, WHAT'LL WE DO?
NIRVANA'S BEEN
FULLY ACTIVATED.
- Natsu: AND IT'S GOT LOTS
OF LEGS. WHOA!
THAT THING TOTALLY LOOKS
LIKE A MONSTER OCTOPUS.
- WHAT?  YOU'RE CRAZY.
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
HOW ABOUT A SQUID?
- SURE, WHATEVER.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME,
SO LET'S JUST
"SQUID" TALKING AND HURRY.
- OH, I SEE
WHAT YOU DID THERE, HAPPY!
NICE ONE.
- HUH?
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy:
I DIDN'T MEAN TO SAY THAT,
IT'S JUST 'CAUSE YOU SAID IT
FIRST. - I'VE GOT NO PROBLEM
TAKING THE BLAME
FOR THAT COMEDY GOLD.
- NATSU, I DON'T THINK
WE CAN BE FRIENDS ANYMORE.