[NARRATOR] As the war
against Tartaros rages on,
our heroes find
themselves tested
by the most fearsome
foes they've seen.
These are the Etherious,
born of the books of Zeref
and led by the devious
Underworld King, Mard Geer.
They will stop at nothing in
their quest to meet their maker.
White Dragon Roar!
[ROGUE]
Shadow Dragon
Slash!
[STING, ROGUE screaming]
[NARRATOR] Two of the Nine
Demon Gates have fallen.
Juvia destroyed Keyes,
despite knowing that the life
of her beloved Gray's father
was linked to his.
But before the necromancy
keeping Silver alive had faded,
he was able to pass two
things on to his son.
First, his burning
desire to kill E.N.D.
And last, the mark of
the Ice Demon Slayer.
Fairy Tail has yet to find
victory without sacrifice.
And if the past is any
indicator of the trials ahead,
then the fighting will only
get more difficult from here.
[GRAY]
I'm an Ice Demon Slayer now.
I swear, I'll kill E.N.D.
That human killed a demon?
Way to go!
She pulled it off.
Juvia!
Bane Particles.
Keyes managed to
contaminate her at least.
One for one. That we can take.
[GAJEEL]
You all right?
I've got you. Hang in there!
I want to see Gray.
Where is he?
He'll be back before
you know it. Don't worry.
Okay.
[CANA]
Hello!
Natsu! Lucy! Happy!
Yo, Erza! Hey, Gray!
[WAKABA]
It's a big guild.
Don't make us call
all your names, okay?
Call out if you can
hear us, will ya?!
[CANA]
Still no response.
[WAKABA] They're probably
just outta earshot.
But Tartaros hasn't
shown up either.
Shouldn't we have drawn some
heat with all that shouting?
And what the hell brought
down their base anyway?
Look, man, I'm about
as stupid as you are,
but it seems to me
like ya just listed off
a bunch'a good things,
so maybe we're winning.
That doesn't mean
there's time to relax.
Whoever's still fighting,
we need to find them
and give them support.
But if we leave now,
what if Levy comes back?
Aw, don't worry, bud.
Jet and Droy will definitely
be able to find her.
[CANA] Maybe Tartaros' grunts
went down with the ship,
but the Nine Gates? No way.
[WAKABA] Which means, we need
to get everyone in one place
as soon as we possibly can.
[ROMEO]
Right.
[DROY] Man, why did Levy have
to run off all by herself?!
[JET] Try not to fall behind.
We gotta find her quickly!
[DROY]
I'm with ya!
[LEVY]
Jet! Droy!
Gajeel? Anyone hear me?
How did I get here?
Hello? I have no idea
where I'm going.
[clattering]
[gasps]
Talk about a dead end.
Least this narrows
down my options.
[BOTH yelling]
[STING yells]
[MARD GEER]
You've convinced me.
It seems some humans are
worthy of the power of dragons.
Yeah, well I'm about to
convince your nose to break.
Prepare. You won't enjoy this.
It's true that humans have
stood against me before,
but none have ever remained
standing for such a long time.
Why, this is the second
best fight I've had
since I arrived here.
I've had enough of your crap!
If you're so damn strong,
then stop playing and prove it!
That acrid human cocktail:
Equal parts bold and foolish.
I used to despise your kind,
but I'm beginning to realize
just how thoroughly entertaining
blind arrogance can be.
Wow, dude. You need a mirror.
Damnit.
His defense is ironclad.
[MARD GEER] Was that
all you boys had in you?
I was hoping you two could
put on a bit more of a show.
We haven't landed a single hit.
And he's still using one
hand to hold that book.
[MARD GEER] If you cannot
entertain me in battle,
then perhaps you could
come up with a dance
to celebrate my victory.
I might spare you if I enjoy it.
[ROGUE] And what exactly
does victory mean to you?
[STING] What's the point of
activating the Faces anyway?
We seek to pave the way
for Lord Zeref's return.
[ROGUE]
Zeref?
[MARD GEER]
I highly doubt your feeble minds
could comprehend
much more than that.
I might as well
explain my motives
to a pair of cockroaches.
Those hateful expressions
illustrate my point perfectly.
Tug at their fragile emotions
and humans become the most
predictable creatures alive.
Am I wrong?
Or are the two of you
about to attack me?
[STING]
Shut your friggin' mouth!
[FRANMALTH] Heh, heh. So once
again, I had to ask myself,
"How much is this gonna cost
us? A lot? A little?" Heh.
You know me.
Quite a bit better
than I would like to.
Yeah, say that to
the hole in my noggin.
He's obviously
trying to buy time,
so we might as well decide how
we're gonna cook him up now.
Yeah, he isn't tasty raw.
If he does deceive us,
I say boil him.
We won't have to hear his
screams once he's submerged.
[FRANMALTH]
Oh! I wouldn't dare lie to you
after hearing that threat!
Not that was planning to before,
but if I had been, phew!
I can't believe I left
Sting and Rogue
to face Mard Geer on their own.
I wonder how they've
fared so far.
Honestly, they'd need a miracle
to win against a foe like him.
[ERZA]
Miracles are nice and all,
but keeping faith in your
friends can do the same work.
[MINERVA (NEO)]
Yeah.
Aw, listen to that, Frosch.
Hearin' her fret for our
boys, it warms my heart.
We frogs are cold-blooded.
Despite the shenanigans that she
pulled at the Grand Magic Games,
I believe that deep down,
she's a good woman.
Aye, sir.
M'lady's awesome.
And her cooking skills
would blow you away.
Seriously?
Can she make broiled mackerel?
It's like my favorite
kind of not raw fish!
Of course she can.
And don't get me wrong,
she makes it real good,
but her smoked
salmon's to die for.
Once you try her sole meunière,
you'll never go raw again!
Wow, ya don't say.
Even the fishies'
names sound tasty.
Ah. When I close my eyes, I
can see the last meal she made.
[LECTOR]
Ahh...
I wish fantasies were edible.
Minerva's a chef? And skilled?
[MINERVA humming]
[laughing]
Are we ready for our yum-yums?!
I think she'd make
an excellent wife.
[LECTOR] You mean for
someone else, right?
[ERZA]
You seem to like it back there.
Perhaps you should stay.
[HAPPY]
Please no!
[PANTHERLILY]
We're sorry!
Holy crap.
Erza has a very commanding
presence, doesn't she?
Yeah, but why are we running?
'Cause when Erza's mad,
she gets scary,
like if you took a
big mean bull and--
Quiet, man. You know
she has ears like a fox.
[LECTOR]
So, while we're on the topic,
I was just wondering, Erza,
how highly would you rate
your culinary technique?
Well,
I'm nothing extraordinary,
but I can make do.
You make do?
As in make someone else
do it for ya, am I right?
Sounds right to me.
I have not enslaved a chef.
Mira and Lisanna enjoy cooking.
And they have
demonstrated that they are
far more skilled at that than I.
I'm kinda startin' to wonder if
you've ever turned on an oven.
Yo, m'lady! We
found her weakness!
Next time she starts sassin' ya,
challenge her to a cook off.
Stick her in the stove!
Well said.
And if she's too
chicken for that,
make it a handwriting contest.
She's really good
at writing bad.
[FRANMALTH]
Just checking,
if there were to be a cooking
contest it'd be later
and not involving me, right?
Why is everything a contest?
Stop being so competitive!
Stop wasting your energy.
I want you at full
strength for our cook-off.
[MINERVA (NEO)] But as for
this unreliable fungus.
The way things are
going we'll chop him up
long before I can school you
in the ways of shrimp etouffee.
I agree.
It'd be nice to get
in some practice in
before the main event,
and that may well prove
to be his better use.
That'd be my worst use!
You don't wanna cook me,
I'd taste like fear.
I'll take you anywhere
you wanna go, honestly!
Sure am glad to be
on their good side.
That shroom needs to
learn when to can it.
Good thing you don't
have any problems
with running your mouth.
Yeah, we're lucky like that.
[PANTHERLILY] Wherever you
are, Gajeel, stay strong.
So what's up? She okay?
She's unconscious, but alive.
[NATSU] We need you to
get her outta here, fast.
Yeah, before the rampage begins.
[LUCY]
I'm on it.
But listen you two, be care--
[NATSU, GAJEEL]
We know.
He'll be back soon.
We're on. Try to keep up.
Piss off.
Fire Dragon Roar!
Sa-whoosh.
[yelling]
Iron Dragon Club!
[TORAFUZAR] Oh? Got your
second wind, have you?
[yelling]
These guys suck.
We should be beatin'
the next ones by now.
No doubt.
You're too weak.
No. We must recognize
their strength.
It's clear that these
wizards aren't human.
They're Dragon Slayers.
[TORAFUZAR] Only the full
might of the Etherious
can conquer such powerful foes!
[TEMPESTER]
Let's end this.
Can you guys turn
into monsters, too?
Hey now, they got serious.
Guess we should
follow suit, then.
Lightning Flame Dragon Mode!
Iron Shadow Dragon Mode!
[TORAFUZAR, TEMPESTER]
True form. Etherious!
[NATSU, GAJEEL yelling]
Did Gajeel... just transform?
How're you doin' that?
Oh, you know. I just
devoured Rogue's Shadow.
Now I'm kickass enough to
destroy your sorry butt.
You talkin' like
a frickin' villain!
You're jealous
'cause I'm stronger!
Laxus' lightning
wrecks Rogue's shadows!
What're you gonna
do, get darker?!
[LUCY]
Uh...
Fine, let's make it interesting!
Whoever beats their opponent
first is the strongest.
We'll count from ten!
[BOTH growl]
There ain't no point in bettin'
if there's nothin' at stake!
And once I'm done wipin'
the floor with ya again,
you'll have to write a song
about how strong and cool I am.
So the bad guys, I
think they're ready.
[BOTH yelling]
[BOTH] Ten, nine, eight,
seven, three, two, one!
[NATSU yelling]
[GAJEEL yelling]
Who have they turned into?
Flame Lotus Exploding
Lightning Blade!
Iron Shadow Dragon Roar!
[yelling]
Are they demons?
[NATSU]
Victory...
[GAJEEL]
Is mine!
[LUCY]
Excuse me?!
What?
That's a very
convenient mistake.
[groans]
Tryin' to cheat your
way to victory, eh?
Maybe you are! I tripped and
my fist fell into your face!
Oh, that makes sense. Explains
why I could barely feel it!
Neither could I!
I thought I'd gotten sucker
punched by a kindergartener!
This is the worst time for us to
fight amongst ourselves, guys.
Gray's my man, Lucy.
[LUCY] Keep your paranoid
sleep talk outta this!
Back off, you skank.
[LUCY]
Seriously, Juvia?!
What do I have to do to
convince you I don't want him?!
I'm still gonna win this!
Fat chance! 'Cause I'm gonna
win my fight and yours!
[TORAFUZAR]
No, You'll both lose.
You'll meet your demise in
the depths of the Underworld.
Dark Deluge!
Natsu! Lucy!
These ruins just keep goin'.
We've been walkin'
around for ages,
and I'm startin to wonder
if we'll ever find 'em.
By the way, does anyone
know what time it is?
Beats me.
But judging from how
sore my feet feel,
I'd say we've been
walking for a few hours.
[rumbling]
[ROMEO]
It's a flood!
But why is the water so dark?
[CANA]
You can ponder that later.
We need to find
high ground, c'mon!
This water. Where's it from?
Could be Tartaros.
It definitely matches
their color scheme.
[GAJEEL, NATSU yelp]
I feel like... I just
heard Gajeel's voice.
This is probably
not my best idea.
[GAJEEL] How much water
did old shark face make?
[LUCY] If we can't find
the surface, we'll drown.
Oh, right! Juvia can
breathe in this, no problem.
[LUCY]
Can't she?
[NATSU]
All right, you!
Not even a spark.
[LUCY] I'm running out
of breath so fast.
It's like this water's
draining my strength.
[LUCY]
Oh, no. I'm gonna black out.
[GAJEEL] How's this guy
so fast underwater?
And why's the other one just
watching? Cocky bastards.
Salamander, listen! You
can't fight in this stuff!
Just take the girls
and find a way out!
[GAJEEL]
Whoa. Salamander's down.
Juvia. Lucy.
[TORAFUZAR] That's what happens
when you swallow this water.
It's lethal to humans. They'll
be dead in five minutes.
Oh, wait.
Your kind needs air to live,
so they'll probably be gone
before the poison's
done its work.
[GAJEEL] If I can take him
out, the water goes too.
[TORAFUZAR] You're out
of your element, slayer.
[GAJEEL]
He's too fast.
[TORAFUZAR]
Deep Impact!
[LEVY]
There he is!
[GAJEEL]
C'mon, get up!
So not only did you
survive Deep Impact,
you're back on your feet.
Very impressive.
At least for a human.
[GAJEEL] One more hit
like that and I'm through.
But prepare to be lost
in a pitch black sea.
[GAJEEL] I can move faster
than him, even underwater.
I just have to be a shadow.
[GAJEEL]
Iron Dragon Sword!
No way. He's too strong.
This is Tartaros!
[GAJEEL]
If I could...
...just breathe.
[GAJEEL]
Damn it. I can't even move now.
I could take this guy...
...if only I had some air.
[GAJEEL]
My vision's fading.
All I can see are black clouds.
[GAJEEL]
This is how I die.
Drowning, falling,
fading into black.
[GAJEEL]
Light? I don't need light.
Air. Give me some air!
[GAJEEL] Screw your
tunnel. I ain't goin'.
[TORAFUZAR]
Uh?
[GAJEEL]
I'm breathing.
Levy?! How did she get here?!
I'll teach you to
meddle in my fights!
[GAJEEL]
Don't you touch her!
[LUCY] Levy's devotion may have
given Gajeel a fighting chance,
but Torafuzar has never met his
match in the Underworld's sea.
Its black, poisonous waters
slowly work their way
into the chinks
of Gajeel's armor,
until he succumbs
to them at last.
But then, right when
all seems to be lost,
Gajeel is struck by a memory
that strengthens his spirit.
Next Time:
"Tartaros Chapter Steel."
Only through our feelings
can we battle despair.