[LAHARL]
Acnologia?
You're sure that's
what Zeref said?
You must be certain!
Damn, I'm useless.
How could I let myself
just get paralyzed by fear?
Hey, get a hold of yourself!
Are you absolutely sure
he said "Acnologia"!
Move! Prepare to withdraw!
All forces,
retreat at once!
As of this moment, our survey
of Tenrou Island is negated!
[CARLA]
Previously, on Fairy Tail.
[HAPPY]
Kaboom!
[PANTHERLILY] Would you
stop making that sound!
[HAPPY]
Sorry!
Now that Laxus is here I'm just
in that kind of mood, you know!
[CARLA]
That's a lie.
You're trying to take advantage
of Lily's fear of thunder.
[PANTHERLILY]
I fear nothing!
[HAPPY]
Kaboom!!!
[PANTHERLILY]
I said knock it off!
[HAPPY]
That's for Natsu becoming
a Lightning Flame Dragon.
[DORANBOLT]
Was this really for the best?
Look, I know how
important the mission is.
However.
I'm also responsible for
the lives of our shipmates.
Retreat is the only option.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
We left so many people behind.
We could have easily pulled
them off of the island.
But instead.
I understand how you feel.
There was a time when
I thought the same way.
But in the end
I realized how naïve I was
and justice demands that-
Oh cut the peace
and justice crap.
All we did here was run away!
It's obvious you're
not thinking logically.
If blaming me
will ease your guilt.
then by all means.
Take out
your frustrations
and be done with it.
No. It's just.
I don't know how
to make things right.
[HAPPY]
"Realm of the Abyss"!
Slice!
How insulting.
Writing of that caliber
can't touch me!
[FRIED] Did you honestly believe
my talents were limited to only
defensive Enchantments?
[YOMAZU]
Say what!
I guess Grimoire
Heart isn't all
that it's cracked up to be.
You're welcome to try
something new, if you like.
Slice!
Perhaps writing
the character for 'learning'
will help you out.
Enchantment!
Your writing is now destroyed!
That arrogance is going
to get you killed someday.
Your Enchantments
have a fatal flaw.
They're long and complicated,
but my writing is simple
and versatile.
Allow me to demonstrate!
It's certainly
louder than the last one.
No, he broke through!
[YOMAZU]
Slice! Roar!
"Roar" is a noun and a verb!
So not only does it
refer to the actual sound,
but it also means to
be heard far and wide!
[FRIED] You strengthened
one character with another.
Interesting.
I'll admit that I
underestimated your abilities.
But what you fail to realize,
is that true expression
derives from the
gathering of words into--
[YOMAZU]
Are we still fighting here?
Is Fried trying to fight
that guy with a lecture?
Or a philosophical debate.
At least he's
distracted for now right?
A sword to the face
can be distracting, too.
Baryon Formation, Babies!
[KAWAZU]
Egg wall!
Golden brown and delicious!
Aw man, that
is so gross!
They'll say the same thing
about you when I'm done,
bok-kah!
It looks like Bixlow's
having some trouble.
We can't just
stand here doing nothing.
I know, but fighting that
big guy drained the last
of our magic power.
Yeah! Levy's got a point!
[ELFMAN] We need a way to get
our strength back, pronto.
And there's a mountain
of protein right there!
Please tell me
you're joking, Bro.
He looks
pretty serious.
Thanks, but
I'd rather starve.
Manly munch!
What a pig BOK!
[BIXLOW]
I'm gonna hurl.
[ELFMAN]
That's much better.
Thanks for the meal, birdbrain!
Now that I've eaten,
I feel like a man again!
I dunno if eating
lightning was a good idea.
I've never seen
anything like this before!
A Lightning Flame Dragon.
This is just like the
time he ate a shard of Etherion.
So now Natsu's able to use
Laxus' power and his attacks?
That's awesome!
[KAWAZU]
Egg Buster!
Cut it out!
[ELFMAN]
I'll show you!
[YOMAZU]
Protect!
Slice!
You shouldn't
push yourself, Elfman!
You're gonna drop
dead if you keep this up.
[ELFMAN]
Like I care about that.
Even if I don't have
enough magic power left
for a full-body Take Over.
This one arm is
all I really need.
[ELFMAN] It's caused
a lot of pain, this arm.
It hurt Lisanna made Mira
cry, and it failed to protect
my partner when she needed it.
So, it may be pathetic,
but I'll put every bit of power
I have into it and beat these
barn yard freaks into next week.
Oh yeah,
we're back, baby!
We'll fight as one unit.
This is your chance
to make it up to Evergreen.
Are you done giving
yourself a pep talk?
You should be savin' your
breath to beg for mercy!
Dark Écriture. Pain!
Alright Babies,
let's fry that chicken!
[TOMMEN A]
Fry the chicken!
[KAWAZU]
I just got scrambled, bok-kah!
Look out, Kawazu!
Wow, They did it!
Incredible.
Look again. It's not over!
So close, and yet so far.
Now it's my turn!
Pierce!
[FRIED] I must say I'm
impressed with your timing.
Finish him off for me would you?
Manly attack!
Where did you come from?!
I have the greatest
big brother ever!
Oh, wow!
Thank your lucky stars
we didn't have to fight him
during the first
part of the trial.
[FRIED] It appears we've
successfully defended everyone.
[BIXLOW] I could sleep
for a week after that.
[ELFMAN]
No kiddin'.
I could definitely use
a nap right about now.
This is what happens to anyone
who messes with Fairy Tail!
I'll make you pay!
Now say, Good bye!
Try hitting me
with your hands tied!
[NATSU]
Lightning Flame Dragon.
Roar!
Look at that!
Oh, man!
That can't be good.
Natsu.
Don't die on us.
I warned ya
not to mess with us.
[LUCY]
Natsu!
Thanks.
That was a close one.
I don't suppose you have any
food tucked away in that outfit,
do ya?
[ERZA] If I used that much
magic power in one go.
I would be toppling over, too.
Another one bites the dust!
We won!
Maybe the power
source is super small
and we just missed it.
Given the size of the ship,
I would say it's highly
unlikely it's being powered
by anything that small.
Is there a reason we're
crawling through the ductwork?
Don't look at me!
Why don't you ask
our fearless leader?
Just a feeling I have.
You'll feel my fist next!
Geez, You could
at least give us a warning
before you stop.
Lily.
What now?
Did you touch it?
Huh?
Carla bopped into my butt,
which means you must've
gotten a face full
of her cushy tushie.
It's not my fault!
You're the one who stopped
without any warning!
[HAPPY] Oh, so it's my fault
that you couldn't stop yourself
from copping a feel?
Lily. Prepare to die!
Would you quit acting
like a child and focus
on the mission at hand?
Besides, it's not
even a big deal!
It might not be a big deal
to you, but it is to me!
I challenge you to a duel!
Would you
Knock it off already!
[CARLA] What made you stop
in the first place, Happy?
Did you see something?
[HAPPY]
Yeah, I did!
Do either of you know
what that thing is?
It's alive!
[HADES] You may have knocked
me down, but I'm not out.
[HADES]
Well done, Makarov.
You've raised some truly
remarkable children despite
your flawed philosophy.
There's no way.
[HADES] I can't remember the
last time someone left me
tattered and torn
after a good brawl.
How is he standing?!
[HADES] I appreciate the
entertainment but I must
get back to work.
I'll be obliterating you now.
Believe me, you'll wish
I'd done so sooner.
What kind of monster could
survive such a powerful attack?
[HADES]
Devil's Eye...
...open.
[HADES] You will now
witness something you've
never seen before.
[HADES]
The Abyss of Sorcery.
[HADES] From here extends an
endless realm that surpasses
your feeble imaginations.
Do you feel that?
It's not real.
No, It can't be!
I've never sensed this much
power in one place before!
And it's getting
bigger by the second!
I am the harbinger of
Fairy Tail's last breath.
You okay?!
[NATSU] No. I've used
up all my strength.
That last attack did me in.
Do you think that's it?
Well, It doesn't really
look like a power source
but who knows?
That's gotta be
the power source.
It's like the heart
of the ship itself.
[PANTHERLILY] Maybe that's
The "Grimoire Heart."
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119A]
I heard voices inside!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119B]
Don't be ridiculous!
How could anyone get in there?
Oh no!
They found us!
I'll try to keep
them occupied.
You two hurry and put that
thing out of commission!
[HAPPY]
Any ideas?
[CARLA]
Break it, of course!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119A] How the
hell did a cat get in here?
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119B]
Who cares?
Just stomp it.
Stomp this!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119A]
You little fleabag!
Now you're askin' for it!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119B]
How'd he get so big?
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119C]
Get him!
[PANTHERLILY]
How generous.
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119D]
But that's my sword!
How're we supposed to break
something that big on our own!
[CARLA] I guess we're just gonna
have to fiddle with things
at random.
[PANTHERLILY] Well this
is certainly unexpected.
I never thought I'd find
a size-changing sword
outside of Edolas.
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119A]
Defend the heart!
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119B] We can't
let him do any more damage!
I Think I'll keep it.
I could use a
replacement for Bustermarm.
[GRIMOIRE SOLDIER 119D]
Aw, c'mon man,
I spent four months pay
on that Musica sword!
[PANTHERLILY]
Bring it on!
Hang on, Happy.
This isn't
over just yet!
Why does everything
we do involve hurting!
Come! Face your death!
[HAPPY] That's it, next time
Natsu wants something destroyed
he can handle it himself.
The Abyss of Sorcery.
Yes. Its power is
overwhelming.
Hey! Snap out
of it. Come on!
No. I can't
I'm out of power.
In order to walk the
path of sorcery one must
sink into its abyss
of eternal darkness.
Within that darkness
lies primordial magic
that shines like the heavens.
The purest of magic power!
[HADES]
Can you feel it?
The primordial magic is
so close it's palpable.
Yet it's so far in the depths it
may as well be out of reach.
Within those depths
is a lost world.
The Grand Magic World!
[HADES] And Zeref is
the key to reaching it.
[HADES] Tonight, Zeref
will awaken and history
will forever be altered.
And then at long last,
the primordial magics.
Will find their
rightful place with me!
We cannot
allow that to happen.
[LUCY] I know I've heard about
this "primordial magic" before.
Mom?
But you will be ostracized.
Only the strong will
be allowed to live.
And you lack the resolve
necessary to reach
into the abyss.
Things are about
to get way worse.
[HADES]
Chapter four.
Verse twelve,
from the Book of Zeref.
Arcane Magic. Nemesis!
No! He's creating some kinda
monsters from the debris!
[HADES] With the magic power
of the Abyss at my command.
I can create nightmares from
the tiniest speck of dust.
[HADES] Devilish dancers
and heavenly arbiters.
Such is the supremacy
of Arcane Magic!
[ERZA] Each one of these demons
is overwhelmingly lethal
in their own right.
How do you kill
pure magic power?
[WENDY]
I'm scared.
Someone, please!
Make them go away!
[ERZA]
I can't stop shaking.
Is this what terror feels like?
[GRAY]
Why do I feel so afraid?
Snap out of it!
[LUCY]
We're done for.
I've never felt so helpless.
It's like all of my
courage has faded away.
[LUCY]
Natsu!
[NATSU]
Don't worry.
We've got everything
we need to beat this guy
right here with us.
There's nothing
wrong with fear.
After all.
How else would we come
to know our own weaknesses?
[GILDARTS and NATSU]
And you need to know them.
to become a stronger
and gentler person.
[NATSU] Today we learned
just how weak we really are.
[NATSU]
So what do we do next?
I'll tell you.
We grow stronger!
[NATSU] On our own we might be
too afraid to stand up to him.
[NATSU] But right now, we
have our friends by our side.
I still have courage because
you're all here with me!
There's no reason to be afraid!
When we're together we
can accomplish anything!
[HADES]
Still holding onto the light?
You fools!
Your future is
nothing but darkness.
[ERZA]
Our friends are by our side.
[GRAY] There's no
reason to be afraid.
[LUCY]
You've given me hope, Natsu.
[WENDY] Even if we have
no magic power left.
[ERZA] We'll keep fighting
until our last breath.
[ERZA] Because that's
the Fairy Tail way!
Let's go!
What could you possibly hope
to do without any magic power?
Now dance!
My devils of the earth!
[HADES] I shall send you
into the depths of darkness!
It's time for
your sun to set.
Fairy Tail!
[HAPPY]
Go, Natsu!
You can take that geezer out!
[NATSU] Don't worry, I'm
gonna make sure he regrets
even thinking about
messing with Fairy Tail!
[HAPPY]
Aye!
So how are you gonna do it?
What's the plan!
[NATSU]
Plan?
There's only one plan
at a time like this!
[HAPPY]
You mean.
[NATSU]
Uh-huh!
The good ol' "Take 'em
by Storm" plan, of course!
[HAPPY] I should've guessed
it wouldn't be original.
[HAPPY] Next time:
"Daybreak on Tenrou Island"!
[NATSU] Awwwww yeah,
I'm all fired up!
It's good to be the Salamander!
[HAPPY]
Get a grip, will you?
[NATSU]
Huh? Oh. Sorry.