[LUCY sighs]
--[LUCY] This is the life!
--[CANA giggles]
Now that the guild's got
its own bath-house,
I might never take
another job again.
Well, with all the
requests we've had
since the Grand Magic Games,
you may not have a choice.
It's true. This is the busiest
that Fairy Tail's been in years.
[LEVY] Which is why
it's so important to relax.
Don't wanna overwork ourselves.
Ah. So is that why you aren't
out with Jet and Droy today?
It wasn't my idea.
But when the boys insisted they
could handle a job on their own,
well, I didn't think
I should argue.
[birds cawing]
[JET]
All right, Droy!
Let's show Levy what we can do!
Not that she's here--
We need to let her know
that we're strong men
who can handle ourselves!
[JET, DROY]
Please save us, Gajeel!
We're completely helpless!
What possessed you
to bring those two?
I didn't invite 'em.
They followed us!
Speaking of team-ups.
Natsu and Gray just went away
on some random job
together without me.
Just the two of them?
Sounds risky.
As crazy as it seems, they've
kinda been getting along lately.
Guess this two-man job'll
put that to the test.
[LUCY] Well, Happy's with 'em,
so maybe he can keep the peace.
Hear that? Sounds
like Natsu and Gray
might actually be growin'
up a little bit, huh?
Yeah, we'll see.
I'm sure Natsu can handle
whatever Gray throws at him.
Can he, now?
A real man can
handle anything!
[MAX, WARREN]
What is that supposed to mean?
What the hell?
I was hoping for some quiet.
I'd be happy to scrub
your back for you.
Huh?
Sure, why not?
I won't let you down.
[FRIED] My, your back
seems a bit stiff, sir.
Shall I massage you as well?
Whatever, man.
[BIXLOW]
Uh.
Hey, if you're givin' out
backrubs, you can count me in.
Go rub your own.
But, what about--?
[CANA] So, Lucy. I have
a question for you.
--[BIXLOW] Uh?
--[LUCY] Uh. Ask away.
[CANA] A little birdy told me
that Natsu felt you up.
That true?
[MAX, WARREN chuckle]
[ROMEO]
Oh man, how embarrassing,
good thing the old
guys aren't here.
Uhh...
U-Uh...
Oh my goodness!
That little birdy was
very descriptive, too.
[LUCY]
"Birdy" my butt.
It was me!
[LUCY]
It wasn't like that!
I was naked, so he
tried to cover me!
With his hands--
--C'mon, Lucy,
--[LUCY whimpers]
there's no need to be shy.
Wow, no wonder he groped you,
just look at these things!
[LUCY]
Uh! Cana, what are you--?
[LUCY yelps]
Uh. You certainly are
in a good mood, Fried.
Nothin' to do with how
close you are to Laxus.
Please, let me work in peace.
Scrub it good, ya hear?
With pleasure.
--[CANA laughs]
--[LUCY yelps]
--[CANA] Whoa, girl!
--[LUCY] Cana, wait!
I should've known the bath
would lead to this stuff.
Where's Wendy?
She would sympathize.
Wendy went with Erza
to help her out on a job.
Oh. And they're by themselves,
too? I wonder what it is.
[MIRAJANE] They left looking
like Christmas had come early.
Apparently the reward involves
some super rare sweets.
--[LAVIAN laughs]
--[ERZA, WENDY grunt]
[squealing]
Greetings! I am-Uh,
my name's Elie!
I master-Er, I am the master
of the Tawn Fu Blasters!
[CROWD jeering]
I can't believe that
I signed up for this.
[CARLA]
Just hang in there, Wendy.
Think about the sweets!
--Pew pew! Bang bang bang!
--Oh, I do love a full house!
Come, Wendy! Together we shall
whip this crowd into a frenzy!
But... aren't we
already doing that?
[cooing]
Hold on.
If Erza's been doing
a job this whole time,
then who's over there?
Don't know.
Yeah, me neither.
Hey there, blondie.
[GROUP gasps]
It's so good to see you.
What?
It's that girl, Flare,
from Raven Tail!
How'd she even get in here?
Get out!
[LUCY]
Wait a second! Cana!
--[splashing water]
--[LUCY yelps]
What's goin' on?
[LAXUS]
Chick drama.
What's your problem, Lucy?
Let's beat her up!
[LUCY] She's not as bad
as you think she is.
She saved my life!
[CANA]
Uh.
Thanks again for that.
I really owe you one.
Um. Well, then.
In that case, let
me wash your body.
Every last inch of it.
[CANA]
Now we're talkin'!
It's awesome over there!
I can barely listen.
Get every last inch
of my body, too.
You can count on me, sir!
So, why are you here anyway?
Because, now that Raven
Tail's been disbanded,
there's nowhere for me.
Aww.
Well, then, why don't
you join up with us?
Really? That's so sweet.
[LUCY giggles]
Huh?
Her in Fairy Tail?
[JUVIA]
Those yearning eyes.
That pallid, clammy skin.
She's like a ginger
version of me!
Uh! She's come to steal
my darling Gray!
Yeah, baby.
You know how I like
my girls, don't ya?
Pale and clammy.
But do you like redheads?
[GRAY]
I love 'em.
You're everything that
Juvia is and more.
[FLARE] How many kids do
you think we should have?
[GRAY]
Ha-ha.
I want however many kids
you can squeeze out, baby.
Hello?
She'll have to pry him
from my clammy, dead hands!
[FLARE]
That's nice, but...
...I don't really
wanna join Fairy Tail.
[GROUP]
Oh, yeah?
Then get the heck
out of our bath!
[LUCY humming]
[LUCY]
That communal bath is awesome!
[PLUE cooing]
[LUCY] It's way bigger
than the one I have at home.
[PLUE cooing]
Maybe I could upgrade.
I could ask the
landlady to reno--
Oh, wait.
I should probably pay the rent
before I ask for any big favors.
[PLUE cries
[LUCY]
But I'm so broke.
[PLUE cries]
[LUCY] Whelp, guess
it's time to get a job.
Welcome home, Lucy!
We just let ourselves in.
It's like déjà vu!
[PLUE hums]
We're sorry for barging in
like this, but no one was home.
Tea's sub-par but
the place is nice.
The last job we
took paid in sweets.
So well, in fact, that we
felt obliged to share.
Would you care
to partake with us?
Sure! That's so nice of you!
[LUCY] So, I take it
the job was a success?
[CROWD jeering]
Well... it was--
A spectacle!
We gave a rousing performance,
to say the least.
Ha, ha! We even received
a standing ovation!
[CARLA] They stood all right,
but it wasn't to cheer.
[LUCY chuckles]
The boys went on a job
right around when we did,
are they back yet?
[LUCY]
Actually, I haven't seen them.
It seems like they
should be done by now.
They should. It has been
three days after all.
I would hate for their
sweets to go bad.
I don't think they went too far,
so maybe we should
go and check on 'em.
I'm not worried in the least,
but I'll come along
since you are.
Good idea.
Given how skilled they are,
I can't help but be alarmed
that they've taken
this long to get back.
[WENDY] You don't think
they ran into trouble, do you?
They're prob'ly fine.
--[door opens]
--[LUCY] Hey, wait!
I-I'm gonna come too!
[LUCY whimpers]
[LUCY]
It's huge!
What is this?
It's the monster from the flier!
[CARLA] Judging from the odor,
I'd say it's been here for days.
[ERZA] They finished their
task; where are they?
[WENDY] I can't make out
their scents in this forest.
All I can smell is damp
soil and... this... guy.
[ALL gasp]
Carla, I-I knew you'd--
[CARLA]
Happy?
--[whimpering]
--[LUCY] Whoa! You okay?
Please, help me, Carla!
I don't wanna die out here-Oh!
[CARLA]
Hang in there!
[groaning]
Has he woken up?
Yes, but he's still
a bit groggy.
[WENDY] He wasn't injured,
but he's completely exhausted.
Do you know where
Natsu and Gray are now?
Why did you guys get split up?
[HAPPY]
It was terrible.
Natsu and Gray, they're--
What?!
Talk to us, Happy,
what happened?!
It's exactly what you'd think.
[NATSU]
Um-Well, well.
Are ya finally admitting defeat?
I knew you wouldn't last.
Ya melted like
an ice cream cone.
[GRAY]
Shut up.
And get over here so I can
kick your flamin' butt!
I'll make you put some clothes
on, ya voyeurous degenerate!
[GRAY] That's a big word
for you, Dragneel!
--No wonder ya used it wrong!
--[NATSU growls]
[NATSU] What're you, cap'n of
the Naked Grammar Knights?
--[WENDY] Oh.
--[ERZA] Well, that makes sense.
[LUCY]
They had us worried, too.
They've been fighting
for three days straight?
They take breaks so they can eat
and sleep between the rounds.
--[GRAY, NATSU grunting]
--[CARLA] Oh.
Well, isn't that cute,
they have a system.
All right. Stand down you two.
Let's just call it a draw.
Come on home, and I'll
give you some sweets--
[ERZA yelps]
[NATSU, GRAY]
We don't want any!
[ALL screaming]
[BOTH grunt]
You're dead.
--[NATSU whimpering]
--Erza?
W-What are you doing here?
[NATSU, GRAY screaming]
[NATSU, GRAY groaning]
[CROWD chatter]
[grunts]
[growling]
I swear, I'm never doin'
a job with that idiot again.
Obviously, I'm never gonna
do a job with you again.
Well, look at that, they
can agree on somethin'!
And we thought
they'd grown up.
[MIRAJANE]
Okay. Thank you.
Uh-oh.
Those quarrelsome ruffians
will be the death of me.
All that talent and they can't
handle a simple monster slaying?
C'mon. They just got
a lot of pent-up energy.
I bet at their age
you were just the same.
[MIRAJANE]
Master.
[MAKAROV]
Hm?
[MIRAJANE] We've just received
an emergency job request.
[MAKAROV grumbles]
Another one?
Ever since the
Grand Magic Games,
we've been getting quite a few
specific requests for wizards.
Yeah, I noticed.
It's kinda like we're
all celebrities now!
Guess the Volwatt job
was an example of that.
In that case, things
were better before.
Hey there, Natsu and Gray!
We got another special job
request for the two of you.
[NATSU, GRAY]
Not happenin'!
They only took
that last job together
'cause they were both requested?
Try to cooperate this time.
If not for yourselves,
then for your guild.
[BOTH growl]
So, it says...
My word!
Is somethin' the matter, Gramps?
I ain't workin' with him,
tell 'em I said no.
But tell 'em I said it first!
Copycat.
You'll go, and while you're
out there, you'll behave.
To the best your feeble
little minds are able.
What's up?
The client who's requested
you is Warrod Sequen.
He's the fourth highest-ranked
of the Ten Wizard Saints.
This makes him one of the
Four Emperors of Ishgar.
[GROUP gasps, murmurs]
If he's a Wizard Saint then
why would he need our help?
It doesn't make sense.
This job must be
super dangerous.
Hmm. I should go with you.
[BOTH]
Uhh.
It's been a nice walk so far.
Yeah! And this
weather is amazing!
Especially with this breeze.
Kinda feels like
we're all goin' out
on a family picnic, doesn't it?
Perhaps it would, if it
weren't for those two.
You ate my jerky, admit it!
As if I'd ever eat
anything you touched!
Shut your mouth
and put a shirt on!
If there's somethin' you don't
wanna see, then stop lookin'!
Simmer down you two.
Master asked that you behave
yourself around this client.
I tagged along so I could
help with that, but honestly?
I'm not sure
that's even possible.
[GRAY, NATSU growling]
Okay, so if I remember
everything correctly,
the Ten Wizard Saints are
chosen by the Magic Council,
but how does someone get
to be an Emperor of Ishgar?
The same way?
That's right.
Master Makarov and
Lamia Scale's Jura
have been Wizard
Saints for years.
Jose of Phantom Lord
once held this title,
but was stripped of it.
For that matter, so was
Jella--I mean, Siegrain,
when he left the Magic Council.
But the Wizard Saints
are far from equals.
The four strongest among them
are called Emperors of Ishgar.
Maybe I should just
go back to the guild.
[WENDY]
What's "Ishgar"?
[ERZA] One of the names
of this continent.
So, one of the strongest
wizards around,
--needs help from these dorks?
--[NATSU growls]
I hope Erza bites
your friggin' head off!
Yeah, well, I hope she rubs
your head in dragon crap!
Well, I hope she...
[ERZA] Why does it feel like
I'm the one being insulted here?
Uh. Hey, I think
that's the house!
Up there, on top of
that hill! See it?
[ERZA]
Good eye.
[LUCY]
Phew. We finally made it.
[HAPPY]
How do we know that's the place?
[CARLA]
We looked at a map.
[LUCY] So this is the
home of Warrod Sequen,
the fourth strongest
of the Wizard Saints!
[NATSU]
Dude lives in a hovel!
[HAPPY]
Talk about shabby!
[LUCY] I was about to say that
it reminds me of your place.
[WENDY]
Is anyone home?
[ERZA]
We've come from Fairy Tail.
About the job request?
[HAPPY]
Whoa.
[CARLA] I've never seen
this many houseplants.
[LUCY]
Excuse me, sir?
[WARROD]
Shh.
[LUCY]
Ah! Sorry!
[WARROD]
Hush.
Be silent, will you?
[GROUP gasps]
[WARROD]
Plants prefer peace and quiet.
So, do me a favor and kindly
shut your wretched mouths!
[yelps]
[GROUP grunting]
Aww. Just kidding!
[BOTH]
Aww.
[GROUP gasping]
C'mon, kids, it was
just a joke! Lighten up!
It's my belief that
plants and flowers
adore the sound
of the human voice!
[laughing]
A tree?
He's definitely not
as funny as he looks.
You tellin' me this
guy's a Wizard Saint?
[WARROD] I bid you welcome,
wizards of Fairy Tail.
Thank you for traveling
such a long way.
Now, tell me, who amongst you
are called Natsu and Gray?
[WARROD]
My goodness!
You're a bit more
feline than I imagined!
[NATSU, GRAY]
Uh...
Got you again!
You're so gullible!
[WARROD laughing]
Well, at least he
cracks himself up.
Uhh. Yeah.
[WARROD laughing]
[GRAY]
He's still laughing at that?
[NATSU] So, can we
make fun of him, or--?
[WENDY] Of course not.
He's like royalty.
All that laughing's
got me thirsty!
[WENDY whimpering]
Pardon me, but we
seek an audience
with a Wizard Saint by the
name of Sir Warrod Sequen,
and need to know
if we've found him.
[WARROD]
Yes.
You now stand before
Warrod Sequen, in the bark.
[ALL grunt]
Naah. I'm just
screwin' with you.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Just kidding again,
it's really me!
[GROUP groans]
This old man's a
real piece of work.
You can say that again.
[WARROD]
I'm retired now.
And since retiring,
I've spent my days
bringing the deserts of
this land back to life.
Retired, you said.
Can I take that to mean you
belonged to a guild once?
[WARROD chuckles]
Yes, and a great guild it was.
But that was a long time ago.
These days my allegiance
is to nature.
Every retired man needs a hobby.
Mine is turning
deserts into forests.
As you can imagine,
I've seen many peculiar things
traveling about the
deserts of this land.
Most recently, I came
across a village
hidden in the Mountains.
As it turned out, I had
read about this place before.
Known as the Village of
the Sun, its people worship
an ever-burning flame
as their guardian deity.
They've got a fire
that never goes out?
[WARROD]
They do.
But when I got there, the
whole place had frozen over.
[GRAY grunts]
[WARROD] Be it by nature,
or the folly of man.
Every person,
plant, and creature.
All the buildings, too.
The river was solid ice.
Even the sacred flame
of the village was frozen,
though it burns on, even now.
It's possible to freeze a flame?
Oh, that poor village.
I have no idea what happened
to the people there.
However, one thing
that was clear to me
is that they're still alive.
[HAPPY] I thought you
said they were all frozen.
[CARLA]
None of this makes sense.
The people of that village
are in dire need of help.
They must be restored.
That is why I called on you.
Break the curse of ice.
That is your task.
No problem!
I'll just melt the stuff!
Those folks're gonna be
nice and toasty real soon!
If that's all you needed, then
why'd you ask for both of us?
Because, this ice
is far from ordinary.
It will take more than
fire alone to melt it.
Huh.
Needless to say, we'll
do as you ask, but--
[WARROD]
Hm?
You're one of the
strongest wizards alive.
Surely if we can handle
this, then so could you.
[WARROD]
I believe you may be under
a certain misconception
about my rank.
[GROUP gasps]
[WARROD]
Despite the heady title,
we Wizard Saints are
far from omnipotent.
We're just ten people
the council chose
to put on top of a list.
There are many wizards on
this continent who surpass me.
And there are wizards
beyond this continent
who surpass even them.
And when you look at it like
that, I'm really no one special.
As a matter of fact,
I have almost no
aggressive spells to speak of.
In a battle of might against
youngsters like yourselves,
I wouldn't stand a chance.
Even so.
[WARROD] Everyone has their
strengths and weaknesses.
This is what inspires
wizards to forge alliances.
And then form guilds.
Wouldn't you agree, my dear?
[ERZA gasps]
[BOTH laugh]
[BOTH growl]
--Aye!
--[laughs]
You're as wise as I imagined.
We accept your job request!
What he said!
You can leave it
to us. We got this!
We'll be glad to help!
[grunts]
[WENDY] So, this "Village of
the Sun," place. Where is it?
[WARROD] About 1200 miles
south, as the crow flies.
[CARLA]
Too bad we aren't crows.
Nonsense, the least I can do
is help you reach the village.
Gather there, all of you.
Be sure that you aren't
leaving anything behind.
What's he gonna do?
Perhaps he has some
sort of magical vehicle.
'Preciate it, but I'm
just gonna walk.
[ERZA]
Suck it up and do as he says.
Now, then.
Everyone ready to go?
[NATSU]
Wait, so it isn't a vehicle?
[WARROD]
Pivot right!
Ha-ha. Just as
gullible as always!
[GROUP]
Hey!
[HAPPY]
Huh?
[WARROD]
I leave this task in your hands,
youngsters of Fairy Tail.
Should you face yourselves
in this journey,
I ask you to look closely.
Do this and you shall
overcome whatever obstacles
may fall before your paths.
[ALL yelping]
[ALL cheering, laughing]
This is amazing!
That it is. He can make
a tree fly like a dragon.
Funny. He's humble,
but his magic is amazing.
The power to control
nature itself.
Time certainly
does fly, doesn't it?
[MAVIS]
Hey, Warrod!
Get over here, will ya? Hurry!
[YURY]
Hey. There he is.
[HADES]
He does like to take his time.
You were off
day-dreamin,' weren'tcha?
Take a look.
There's one dream come true.
Whoa. Amazing.
[WARROD]
It's our very own Guild.
[YURY]
Sure is.
[MAVIS] Let's take a picture
so we never forget this!
[MAVIS] The day that
Fairy Tail was born!
[WARROD]
A 105 years it's been.
And you know what?
Our Guild has barely
changed at all.
Mavis, those youngsters
have inherited your spirit.
[LUCY]
Thanks to Warrod's magic,
we were able to get to
the Village of the Sun
in almost no time!
But now that we're here,
we've found a bit more
than we initially expected.
Not only is this village
encased in magical ice,
it's also the ancient home
of a pretty major secret.
And on top of that, ours isn't
the only group of outsiders
that thinks it has
business here.
Next Time:
"Wizards vs. Hunters."
This other group? They're
called Sylph Labyrinth!