[LUCY] After being
disbanded for a year,
the Fairy Tail members
were finally reunited.
But we were still missing
Master Makarov,
who had been taken prisoner
by the Alvarez Empire,
an ocean away.
The ruler of this land was
none other than Zeref,
who is bent on obtaining
the Fairy Heart.
A sacred lacrima containing
the body of our founder
and first master,
Mavis Vermillion.
With it, he will be able to
harness unlimited magic power.
On the heels of
Makarov's rescue,
the Alvarez Army invaded
Ishgar, and the war began.
As we struggled against
the incredible might
of Zeref's elite force known
as the Spriggan Twelve,
our allies in guilds
across the land,
rushed in to join the fight.
Natsu took on Zeref himself.
During this intense clash,
he learned who he truly is:
Zeref's younger brother.
As well as E.N.D.,
the strongest demon from
the Black Wizard's book.
This makes things more
difficult because it means
if Natsu were to kill Zeref,
he would die, too.
The war raged on at
a dizzying speed
as Acnologia entered the fray,
taking down a member of the
Spriggan Twelve, God Serena.
After seeing Natsu and Lucy
work together in battle,
Mavis devised a strategy
for defeating Zeref
once and for all.
She then asked Cana
to use Fairy Glitter
to attack her projection,
destroying her lacrima
and enabling her
to regain her body,
which had been trapped
for nearly a century.
Natsu's team traveled
with Brandish
as she tried to convince
her fellow Spriggan,
the "Wizard King" August,
to stop fighting,
but Mest's scheme ruined
any chance for peace.
Meanwhile, Acnologia
confronted Irene,
another powerful Spriggan,
who cast a spell known
as Universe One.
This restructured the
geography of Fiore
and displaced everyone
in the kingdom.
The guild members were
scattered throughout the land,
but the voice of Mavis'
childhood friend Zera
guided them back to
Fairy Tail's guild hall.
Zeref has now captured Mavis,
and is waiting for our return
alongside every one
of the Spriggan Twelve.
Both living and dead.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Yo.
--It's Gildarts! Ha!
--[HAPPY laughs]
[LUCY chuckles]
I'm feelin' hungry.
I wanna go back to the guild
hall and have a snack.
[stomach growls]
The old man's here!
I knew we'd see him
again someday!
Awesome!
Oh, wow!
[FAIRY TAIL cheering]
That's what I call
serious backup.
I'll say!
Always been your style
to just show up
whenever you please, huh?
Don't I know it.
Hi, Cana. My sweet baby girl!
Ew. Let go of me!
And pay attention to the enemy!
Oh, yeah. This guy.
[GILDARTS]
His magic power feels weird.
Like it's coming from
a corpse or somethin'.
[GOD SERENA]
Say what?
Too bad, really.
If you were alive, you'd
be one hell of a wizard,
but like this,
you're a punchline.
[laughs]
You like to run your
mouth, don't you?
Soon you'll stand in awe
of the might of "Eight
Dragon" God Serena!
Oh, whoa! So much magic power!
From a headbutt? That's crazy!
[NATSU]
So cool!
Hey, Romeo, are you okay?
Well, honestly? No, not really.
I was so pumped up before.
I thought I could handle this.
But now...
[ROMEO] I realize how horribly
we're outnumbered,
and I'm terrified.
It's pathetic.
My knees are shaking like crazy.
I feel like I can't even walk.
Don't feel bad,
we're all scared.
But we can stay strong together.
[SOLDIER C]
A sandstorm?
[SOLDIER D]
Where did it come from?
[SOLDIER E]
I can't see anything!
Hey, Fairies! Time for you
to shrivel up and die!
That guy again?
Yes, and he's using the
same spell as before!
A real man isn't
afraid to get dirty!
Elfman!
[ELFMAN]
I'll handle this jackass!
His dusty ol' attacks won't
work against my Sand Beast!
A big oaf like you will
sink like a stone!
Antlion Pit!
[yelling]
That was a freakin'
manly save, Lisanna!
You can fly away,
but you'll never escape
the Spriggan Twelve!
Right then. I'll make the
lot of ya disappear.
Sorry, but you're gonna
have to deal with me!
[FAIRY TAIL]
Go, Mira!
[JACOB] I like your spunk,
but you've made me very angry!
Whoa! So indecent!
Whoopsie!
[WALL chuckles]
Oh, yeah! Although it's a lot
of fun playing judge and jury,
my very favorite role
is executioner!
[WALL]
It's boom-boom time!
[laughing]
Huh?
I don't like all these
insects in my territory.
[YUKINO]
Rogue and Minerva are here!
We are, to render aid.
Thank you. Where's
Master Sting?
We became separated
after the sky lit up.
But I'm not worried.
He can handle himself.
I'm curious how the two of you
were able to find your way here.
We were lucky to have
this girl guide us.
[WALL chuckles]
More wizards for
us to devastate!
Do you feel their strange
magic power, Milady?
It's quite odd. I believe
they may be dead.
Which means somebody's
controlling them.
Yukino, will you deal with that?
[YUKINO]
Of course!
[ANGEL] It's amazing how
nice you are to people
who aren't even in your guild!
[MINERVA] Just who is
this overly sappy girl?
[YUKINO]
Uh. Long story.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Look at 'em all go!
Everyone's trying to clear
a path for the guild!
You better get outta my way!
[SOLDIER A]
You won't move past us!
[SOLDIER B] We'll defend
His Majesty to the death!
How does he keep
shattering my attacks?
It's a damn shame.
I wish I coulda fought ya
at your original strength.
Purifying Truth... Firmament!
[GOD SERENA screaming]
[ALL laugh]
I hope you're ready, guys!
We're headin' to the guild hall!
Yeah, let's go!
[ROMEO yelling]
[MAVIS groaning]
You poor little creature.
The thing that set you
apart was your intellect,
and that's been stripped away.
Invel's Ice Slave spell robs a
person of their sense of self.
Your inner voice muffled
as if through a thick sheet
of impenetrable ice.
How long will it
take to complete
your separation enchantment?
You understand
more than anyone
this girl has a very
special power
and that this won't be quick.
[groaning]
I only wish to keep her
suffering to a minimum.
[IRENE]
Oh?
I never imagined
you would express
such sympathetic
feelings, Your Majesty.
This may come across
a bit insolent,
but I assure you I
mean no disrespect.
You won't beat
Acnologia with mercy.
Only with cunning
and brute strength.
He is the epitome of darkness.
The true Dragon King.
You have a gift for
speaking truth to power.
I'll take my leave.
[screams]
Excuse me, my lady.
Clearly, I'm a bit occupied
at the moment, Neinhart.
Can you wait to discuss
your problem later?
It's about Erza. I've found her.
[IRENE]
So she survived. As I expected.
What do you advise I do?
I felt I had to consult
you before acting.
Kill her.
But--
You know I take no pleasure
in repeating myself.
I hear you.
However, my
Historias have proven
to be completely
ineffective against her.
Then you must go and fight
her yourself, obviously.
You do remember who
you are, don't you?
Remember who I am?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ERZA yells]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Now follow me!
[WIZARDS cheering]
She's so incredibly brave.
She's like a flower
that blooms in battle.
[yells]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Watch out! You'll
take everyone down!
Come on, Cana, you're
gonna make me blush.
[CANA]
It wasn't a compliment!
[AJEEL]
Why are you just standing there?
Do you want me to put you
out of your misery, or what?
[ELFMAN]
Get back, Lisanna!
Oh, my. I can't look!
It's too racy!
You're bein' kinda
rude, you know?
[ROGUE] I'll knock away
your Bane Particles!
The alchemist is
no match for me!
[NATSU yelling]
Fire Dragon Roar!
[gasps]
What the hell'd ya
do that for, Gray?
I didn't do anything!
It's weird. The air is changing.
Cold.
You should try wearing
some clothes, Lucy.
[HAPPY shivers]
--[NATSU, GRAY gasp]
--It's freezing!
[JUVIA]
I'm going numb!
Let's fire it up!
What? No way.
[GRAY]
Natsu!
Lucy! Juvia!
[INVEL] Ah. It would seem
you're resistant to cold.
I'll freeze you out!
[groans]
[screams]
[GRAY]
What's going on?
I'm Invel Yura, Winter General.
A title I've earned
for obvious reasons.
You may handle the chill,
but I bring winter itself.
[GRAY]
No. How can this be happening?
I actually feel cold.
It's like... the blood in
my veins is freezing.
[MAVIS]
Someone help me.
Invel must be defeated...
or I'll be lost forever.
Ice Make Magic Ice Shield!
Ice Make Magic... Ice Impact!
Ice creation magic, I see.
It's no wonder you have
an immunity to the cold.
[GRAY]
I don't believe it.
He froze my ice spell?
I use ice magic in a
more absolute sense.
Not merely creating
objects from ice.
Instead, freezing everything
to its very core.
This "maker" magic you wield
is an inferior derivative
of true ice wizardry.
I can shatter your spells
with barely any effort.
Is that so?
Then what about this?
I got it from my father.
The power to slay demons!
[INVEL gasps]
This is how I'm
gonna kill E.N.D.!
[GRAY]
Ice Demon Zero Long Sword!
[yells]
[INVEL groans]
How can this be?
I've never seen it before.
Demon Slayer magic?
[INVEL] He can use it to
create powerful magic weapons,
but it seems like there's
a steep cost involved.
As if it's taking something
away from him.
Perhaps this power
robs the wielder
of their very own humanity.
How fascinating.
[yells]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
What's going on?
It's snowing?
Feels more like
a blizzard to me!
[WIZARD D]
First we had a sandstorm.
Now this?
Invel's doing.
[GRAY]
It's so cold.
But I can't let him
freeze me. I gotta fight!
You're unique.
I believe you have what
it takes to be one of us.
Surely you must've
noticed this by now,
but your heart is slowly
filling with darkness.
[GRAY] What? I ain't gonna
listen to this crap!
Magic grew from the darkness.
The abyss of sorcery.
This is why His Majesty
uses it himself.
So that means you guys actually
see yourselves as villains, huh?
[INVEL] Our side has no
concept of good or evil.
Darkness is a powerful force
that exists inside everyone,
regardless of your creed.
It's strong in you.
You can barely contain it.
[GRAY] That's it. I've
heard enough of this!
If you knew me at all,
you'd know I've never been much
of a "white knight" type.
I'll protect my
Fairy Tail family
by doing whatever
the hell I gotta do!
[NATSU]
You tell 'im, Gray!
[BOTH gasp]
Because that's the
Fairy Tail way!
I'm not a popsicle anymore!
Owie! Please, stop!
Gray, my love, are you okay?
[GRAY]
You guys!
[INVEL]
Natsu managed to melt my ice.
I suppose it makes sense
considering his origin.
All right, it's our turn now!
I say we give him
a Fairy stampede!
Whoa!
[GRAY]
Hey! What the--? Put 'em down!
[NATSU]
Uh! Yeah!
[LUCY]
What are you doing?
I'm taking what's
rightfully mine.
Like hell you are! Let us go!
I realize you're mad, Brandish,
but we didn't know--
Be quiet.
[GRAY]
Get back here!
What're we supposed to do now?
[gasps]
Juvia.
Gray, darling.
[gasps] I feel so weird.
Like my head is
spinning outta control.
I can't move at all.
It's like my body refuses to.
It's Ice Lock.
It constrains your mind, thus
turning you into my puppet.
Regardless how you may feel
inside, you will do my bidding.
You will fight to the death.
Kill each other?
[INVEL] Yes, and you will
remain in these shackles
until one of you dies.
This won't hold me.
Screw you!
[gasps]
[GRAY]
I can't...
[INVEL]
This is perfect.
I know Gray will
prevail in this fight.
And at the very moment
he kills his friend...
...the darkness in him
will take over.
His Majesty won't be
the one to defeat E.N.D.
Gray will do it, I've no doubt.
Juvia.
Gray, dear.
[JUVIA]
No. I refuse.
I can't hurt
the love of my life!
Instead, while I still
have a little control...
...I'll have to kill myself!
[LUCY]
Invel, AKA "the Winter General,"
makes a move to force Gray into
releasing his inner darkness.
He begins by taking over
Gray and Juvia's minds,
making them fight to the death.
Struggle as they might,
their hearts freeze and
their thoughts slip away.
However, Juvia never loses touch
of her feelings for Gray,
and fights back the only
way she knows how.
Next time: "Gray and Juvia."
Their path to the
future is murky,
but will love light the way
through the shadows?