- WOW. I KNEW WE'D LOOK ALIKE,
BUT SEEING HER IS
FREAKING ME OUT.
- IS SHE THE EDOLAS
VERSION OF ME?
- ( gasps )
- THERE THEY ARE.
- OVER THERE.
- I'M AFRAID THE INTRODUCTIONS
WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
- IF WE STAY HERE,
WE'RE ALL GONNA GET CAUGHT.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ALL RIGHT, NATSU,
DO WHAT YOU DO BEST.
- WITH WHAT, EXACTLY?
- WITH YOUR MAGIC, OBVIOUSLY.
YOU'RE A WIZARD, RIGHT?
- WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO USE
OUR MAGIC SINCE WE GOT HERE.
- WHA...
- HOLD UP. HOW COME YOU
CAN STILL USE YOURS?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- LUCY, YOU'RE OUR ONLY HOPE.
- GIVE THOSE BRUTES
THE WHAT FOR.
- IF WE GET CAPTURED,
THEN ALL OUR FRIENDS
ARE AS GOOD AS DEAD.
- SO, THIS MEANS, I'M THE
STRONGEST ONE IN FAIRY TAIL.
- QUIT FANTASIZING
AND TAKE THEM OUT.
- Happy: FIREBALL.
- NOW OPEN,
GATE OF THE WHITE RAM, ARIES.
- UM, HELLO. LEAVE EVERYTHING
TO ME. I'LL DO MY VERY BEST.
- THE FLUFFY ONE.
- WHOA, WHAT KIND OF
MAGIC IS THAT?
- THAT GIRL CAME OUT
OF THIN AIR.
- IT'S A DEMON.
- DOES MAGIC LIKE THAT EXIST?
- ALL RIGHT, ARIES, YOU THINK
YOU CAN TAKE THESE GUYS?
- WELL, I, I'LL CERTAINLY TRY.
WOOL BOMB.
- IS THIS AN ATTACK?
- SO COMFY.
- OH, NO. I DON'T THINK
IT'S WORKING, LUCY.
I'M USELESS, AFTER ALL.
- OH, IT'S WORKING ALL RIGHT.
LET THEM HAVE ANOTHER VOLLEY.
- GO, WOOL SHOT.
- IF THIS IS BEING BEATEN UP...
- THEN BEAT ME EVERY DAY.
- ONE MORE PLEASE.
- ( yelling )
- NOW, WOOL WALL.
- I COULD GET USED TO THIS.
- THIS IS OUR CHANCE TO RUN.
- WAS THAT TO YOUR LIKING?
I'LL BE SURE TO DO
BETTER NEXT TIME.
- TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, LUCY.
- WAY TO WRECK IT, MISS FLUFFY.
- THAT'S ONE WAY
TO TAKE OUT AN ARMY.
- WOW. I'M STRONG,
FOR REAL. THIS ROCKS.
- SO, THIS IS THE POWER
OF EARTHLAND MAGIC?
- WHILE WE HAVE THIS MOMENT,
WE SHOULD FIGURE
OUT OUR NEXT MOVE.
- OKAY, YOU WANNA TELL US
HOW YOU WERE ABLE
TO EVEN GET TO EDOLAS
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- OH, YEAH. WE WERE
WORRIED ABOUT YOU
'CAUSE WE HEARD THAT
EVERYONE IN THE GUILD
WAS TURNED INTO A GIANT LACRIMA.
- HOROLOGIUM AND
MYSTOGAN RESCUED ME
JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
- YOU MEAN THE OLD CLOCK MAN?
- MYSTOGAN WAS THERE?
- CO- KO.
- HEY. WHAT IN THE HECK HAPPENED
HERE? ARE WE STILL IN MAGNOLIA?
- MY APOLOGIES. IN
THE HEAT OF THE MOMENT,
I LACKED THE TIME TO EXPLAIN
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
IF I HAD NOT ACTED AS I DID,
YOUR FATE WOULD BE THE SAME
AS YOUR GUILD MATES.
- THEIR FATE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- I SENSED A DISTORTION
IN THE FABRIC OF SPACE-TIME.
FEARING FOR YOUR SAFETY,
I USED MY OWN POWER
TO APPEAR. I PROTECTED YOU
BY PLACING YOU INSIDE ME.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
ALL THE OTHERS?
DID ANYBODY ELSE IN
THE GUILD MAKE IT OUT
OR AM I THE ONLY ONE?
- I'M TERRIBLY SORRY, MISS LUCY.
I'M AFRAID I DO NOT KNOW
THE ANSWER TO THOSE QUESTIONS.
- I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU
MADE IT OUT ALL RIGHT.
- DO NOT FEAR I AM MYSTOGAN.
- MYSTOGAN?
- TO SAVE OUR FRIENDS,
YOU WILL NEED TO ACT QUICKLY.
- Carla: INCREDIBLE.
- Natsu: HE SURVIVED
THE GIANT SPACE VACUUM, TOO?
- Lucy: YEAH. THEN HE GAVE
ME THE RUN-DOWN
OF WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON.
WAIT A MINUTE. THEY WERE TAKEN
TO ANOTHER WORLD?
THAT'S THE CRAZIEST
THING I'VE EVER HEARD!
- I WISH I HAD MORE TIME TO
EXPLAIN BUT WE LACK THAT LUXURY.
IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE
THE ENTRANCE TO EDOLAS CLOSES.
- LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU WANT ME TO GO THROUGH
THAT HOLE IN THE SKY
TO ANOTHER WORLD?
- MORE OR LESS. IT'S UP TO YOU
TO RESCUE OUR FRIENDS.
WHILE YOU'RE DOING THAT,
I WILL REMAIN HERE AND SEE IF I
CAN FIND ANY OTHER SURVIVORS.
- YOU'LL NEED TO EAT
ONE OF THESE.
- HUH? WHAT ARE YOU...
- I'M SORRY, BUT WE CAN'T DELAY
ANY LONGER. MAKE HASTE.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO
START LOOKING FOR EVERYONE.
- GO, LUCY. YOU CAN DO THIS.
- ( screams )
- ( gasps )
- THIS IS EDOLAS?
THEN I STARTED SEARCHING
FOR ANYONE I MIGHT KNOW
AND EVENTUALLY RAN
INTO THE FIVE OF YOU.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW COME MYSTOGAN IS THE ONLY
ONE WHO KNOWS ABOUT EDOLAS?
- I'D LIKE TO KNOW
WHO THAT GUY REALLY IS.
- IF WE'RE LUCKY,
WE MAY GET TO ASK HIM.
- WELL, I'D LIKE TO KNOW
WHY YOUR MAGIC WORKS
IN EDOLAS AND OURS DOESN'T.
- WELL, MAYBE I'M A LEGENDARILY
BEAUTIFUL HEROINE IN THIS WORLD.
- DON'T THINK SO.
- CAN'T A GIRL HAVE A DREAM?
- I WISH I KNEW THE ANSWER
TO THAT QUESTION.
IF NATSU REALLY CAN'T
USE ANY OF HIS POWER,
I DON'T KNOW HOW
WE ARE SUPPOSED TO WIN.
- SO, YOU BONEHEADS STILL
WANNA TAKE ON
THE KINGDOM ALL BY YOURSELVES?
- OF COURSE, WE DO.
- IF WE DON'T SAVE OUR
FRIENDS, WHO WILL?
- IS THAT REALLY
SUCH A HARD THING TO BELIEVE?
- YOU'LL FIGHT THEM,
EVEN THOUGH YOU CAN'T
USE ANY MAGIC? THAT'S SUICIDE.
- ARE YOU DEAF? ONE OF US
STILL HAS AN ENTIRE ARSENAL.
THAT'S RIGHT, EVERYONE,
JUST SIT BACK
WHILE FAIRY TAIL'S STRONGEST
MEMBER TAKES CARE
OF THIS PROBLEM BY HERSELF.
- OH, YEAH, I'M ALL FIRED UP.
- WE'RE TOTALLY
SCREWED, AREN'T WE?
- I SUPPOSE WE'LL JUST
HOPE FOR THE BEST.
- AYE, SIR.
- YOU'VE GOT THIS
IN THE BAG, LUCY.
- ( giggles ) SO,
WHICH ONE OF YOUR SPIRITS...
- Lucy: THESE GUYS ARE
A BUNCH OF WHACK-JOBS
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
I FEEL LIKE THEY MIGHT CHANGE
THIS WORLD FOR THE BETTER.
I MUST BE GOING CRAZY.
- HOPEFULLY, WE CAN FIGURE OUT
WHERE WE'RE GOING
IF WE USE THIS MAP.
- THAT'S WEIRD. IT LOOKS WAY
MORE LIKE EARTHLAND
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
- THIS IS WHERE WE LAST
SAW THE EDOLAS FAIRY TAIL.
THE GIANT FROG BEAST CHASED US
SOMEWHERE IN THIS VICINITY.
LOUEN, IS WHERE WE RAN
INTO EARTH LAND LUCY.
AND WE'RE CURRENTLY HOLED UP
HERE, IN THE PORT CITY OF SYCCA.
WE'LL HAVE TO SECURE
PASSAGE OVERSEAS
IF WE'RE TO REACH
THE ROYAL CITY.
- OUR FRIENDS
ARE HALF A WORLD AWAY.
- AND THAT'S HALF A WORLD
FILLED WITH ROYAL ARMY SOLDIERS.
WE'LL BE DODGING AROUND
EVERY CORNER.
IT COULD TAKE US WEEKS
TO GET EVEN NEAR THE CAPITAL.
- WOW, THIS IS NUTS.
SHE'S JUST LIKE ME.
WE'VE EVEN GOT THE EXACT SAME
FRECKLES ON OUR BUMS.
- OH, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I DON'T HAVE FRECKLES ANYWHERE.
- WAIT, SCARY LUCY.
DID YOU FORGET
NATSU IS IN THE ROOM?
- I CAN SEE HIM FINE,
HALF-PINT. I JUST DON'T CARE.
- YOU SHOULD!
- TALK ABOUT A MAJOR ACT
OF DUP- LUCY- TY.
- TOMCAT, YOU'RE NOT TO SPEAK
FOR THE REST OF THIS JOURNEY.
- ( groans )
- YOU SEE SOMETHING YOU LIKE?
I'LL SHOW YOU MORE.
- DON'T YOU DARE!
- HEY, WHAT THE HECK ARE
YOU LAUGHING AT? I GET IT.
YOU WERE GONNA POKE FUN AT ME
BY SAYING OTHER LUCY
HAS A BETTER FIGURE, IS THAT IT?
WELL, IF YOU WANNA DIE TODAY,
BE MY GUEST.
- I WAS JUST THINKING, YOU COULD
TOTALLY WASH YOUR OWN BACK NOW.
- Both: HE'S SUCH A CHILD.
- THE TWO OF YOU LOOK
SO MUCH ALIKE,
IT'S KIND OF HARD TO
TELL WHICH IS WHICH.
- I'M PRETTY SURE MY CABOOSE
IS IN BETTER SHAPE.
- WOULD YOU KNOCK IT OFF?
- YOU GUYS SHOULD
TOTALLY COME UP
WITH A MIRROR
IMPRESSION ACT TOGETHER.
- Both: NOT HAPPENING!
- WOW, THEY'RE EVEN
IN PERFECT SYNC.
- PERFECTLY ANNOYING.
- ACTUALLY, THIS REMINDS ME
OF WHEN GEMINI IS AROUND.
- YEAH. NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT.
- GERM- A- WHAT?
- A COUPLE OF CELESTIAL SPIRITS
I'M CONTRACTED WITH.
THEY CAN TURN INTO PERFECT
LOOK- ALIKES OF OTHER PEOPLE.
- OPEN, GATE OF
THE TWINS, GEMINI!
- TA- DA. GEMINI,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
- WHOA.
- IF YOU THOUGHT TWO WAS GREAT,
TRY A TRIPLE DOSE OF HOTNESS!
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THE REST OF YOU,
BUT I THINK THIS WOULD
MAKE FOR ONE AWESOME
GUESSING GAME AT A PARTY.
- AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR "WHO'S THE REAL THING?"
- HELLO, I'M THE REAL LUCY.
- NOPE, I'M THE REAL ONE.
- THEN AGAIN, IT COULD BE ME.
- ALL RIGHT FOLKS, USE THE
BUZZER TO MAKE YOUR CHOICES.
- All: YOU JUST
LOST THE GAME BIG TIME.
- THEY ALL SEEM REAL TO ME.
- I HAVE ONE QUESTION.
WHEN DID YOU PLAN ON
CLOTHING YOURSELF?
- ( screams ) I'M STILL NAKED.
- EVEN WITHOUT GEMINI AROUND,
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO TELL
WHICH ONE OF YOU IS WHICH.
- I DON'T SUPPOSE YA GOT
ONE OF THOSE GHOST THINGS
THAT'S GOOD WITH
A PAIR OF SCISSORS, DO YA?
- YEAH. IN FACT, I HAVE THE
PERFECT SPIRIT FOR THAT JOB.
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE YOU CALLED ME, BABY.
- ARE YOU COOL WITH HIM
CALLING YOU 'BABY' LIKE THAT?
- IF YOU'VE GOT
A PROBLEM WITH HIM,
THEN YOU'RE GONNA FREAK
WHEN YOU MEET TAURUS.
- BOP! SHOO! WOP!
I HOPE YOU LIKE
YOUR NEW DO, BABY.
- THERE SHOULDN'T BE ANY
TROUBLE TELLING US APART NOW,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY
WITH CHOPPING IT OFF?
- I MEAN, MINE TOOK
FOREVER TO GROW OUT.
- YEAH, IT'S JUST HAIR.
- IT'S NOT SERVING SOME
GREAT PURPOSE BY BEING LONGER,
SO WHY DOES IT MATTER?
- BECAUSE EVERY LADY
SHOULD HAVE PRIDE
IN THE "DO" THEY SPORT, BABY.
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
IN A WORLD LIKE THIS YOU TEND
TO FORGET THE LITTLE THINGS,
LIKE 'BOY' OR 'GIRL,' THAT
SEPARATE YOU FROM YOUR FRIENDS.
IN THE END, WE'RE ALL
JUST SURVIVORS.
- IF IT'S THAT TOUGH,
WHY DID EVERYONE IN YOUR
GUILD SEEM SO CARE FREE?
- WELL YEAH, OF COURSE
THEY DID.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO
KEEP YOUR SPIRITS UP
EVEN IF YOU GOTTA FORCE THEM
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
AND WHEN WE CAN'T BRING
OURSELVES TO SMILE,
WE REMEMBER THERE ARE PEOPLE
IN THIS WORLD WHO NEED US.
EVEN IF THAT MEANS
WE'RE LABELED A DARK GUILD.
FAIRY TAIL WILL ALWAYS
BE THERE TO LEND A HELPING HAND.
- BUT, I GUESS THAT STILL
ISN'T ENOUGH IN THE END.
- HUH?
- NOTHING. I'M JUST RAMBLING.
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
I CAN'T BELIEVE MYSELF!
- WELL, YOU'RE CERTAINLY
ENERGETIC FIRST THING
IN THE MORNING, AREN'T YA?
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- LITTLE MISS ME PACKED
HER BAGS AND TOOK OFF
ON US LAST NIGHT.
- "KEEP WALKING FOR
THREE MORE DAYS
AND YOU'LL GET TO
THE ROYAL CITY."
"I'M GONNA GO BACK
TO MY GUILD NOW.
GOOD LUCK AND TRY
NOT TO GET BUSTED."
- WHAT WAS ALL THAT ABOUT
'LENDING A HELPING HAND'?
IF I GET MY HANDS ON HER
I'LL WRING HER SCRAWNY NECK.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT YOU
HAVE A SCRAWNY NECK, TOO?
- SHUT UP!
- THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
OTHER LUCY SAID
SHE WASN'T GONNA FIGHT
AND WE SHOULD RESPECT THAT.
- YEAH.
- YOU'RE SAYING I SHOULD
JUST FORGIVE THIS?
SOMEONE WITH MY FACE SHOULD
NEVER ABANDON PEOPLE IN NEED!
- Natsu: AH, COME ON,
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
- Lucy: IT IS, TOO.
- ( screams )
- "THEY MIGHT CHANGE
THIS WORLD FOR THE BETTER", HUH?
WHAT A JOKE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW LAZY I'VE GOTTEN.
CHANGE SHOULDN'T BE BROUGHT
ABOUT BY OUTSIDERS.
IT SHOULD BE DONE
BY THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE HERE.
IF THEY CAN PULL OFF
THIS SUICIDE RESCUE PLAN
OF THEIRS, MORE POWER TO
THEM. BUT THEY SHOULDN'T BE
THE ONLY ONES TAKING
THE KINGDOM DOWN A PEG.
IT'S TIME FOR THE FAIRY TAIL
OF EDOLAS TO QUIT
RUNNING FROM OUR PROBLEMS.
I'LL CONVINCE EVERYONE
TO STAND UP AND FIGHT
FOR THIS WORLD TOGETHER.
- ( people chattering )
- Male: DID YOU HEAR?
THEY'RE GONNA EXTRACT
MAGIC POWER
FROM THAT HUGE
LACRIMA IN TWO DAYS.
- YEAH. IT KIND OF FREAKS
ME OUT, TO BE HONEST.
I MEAN, WHERE'D THEY HARVEST
ALL THAT POWER FROM?
AN ALIEN WORLD OR SOMETHING?
- I HOPE THEY KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE DOING OUT THERE.
MESSING WITH MAGIC POWER
LIKE THAT COULD BE TROUBLE.
- CAREFUL. SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE YOU'RE QUESTIONING
THE METHODS OF OUR GREAT KING.
- NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT
I MEANT AT ALL. I'M LOYAL!
- RELAX. DON'T WORRY.
EVERYTHING WILL WORK
OUT IN THE END.
JUST LEAVE IT TO HIS MAJESTY,
AND EDOLAS WILL BE
SITTING PRETTY.
- Both:
INTERESTING CONVERSATION.
- YOU THREE PUNKS
MIND TELLING ME
WHAT YOU KNOW IN DETAIL?
- HUH?
- ( humming )
- Happy: WELL, SHE'S
NOT SCREAMING ANYMORE.
IT'S GOOD TO KNOW YOU CAN
CHEER LUCY UP
JUST BY GIVING HER A
RARE BOOK TO READ.
- SO, WHAT BOOK DID YOU
END UP BUYING, ANYWAY?
- A COMPLETE HISTORY
OF EDOLAS, SILLY.
- DON'T YOU WANT TO LEARN
MORE ABOUT THIS AMAZING WORLD
WHILE WE HAVE THE CHANCE?
- NOT REALLY.
- YOU KNOW THE SAYING,
'KNOWLEDGE IS POWER'?
WELL, THIS BOOK HAS GOT
TONS OF IT.
FOR EXAMPLE, THERE'S A TON
OF HISTORY
REGARDING A FEARSOME TRIBE
CALLED THE "EXCEEDS"!
- OH, WE ACTUALLY HEARD
ABOUT THEM ALREADY.
EVERYONE GOT REALLY SCARED
WHEN THEY STARTED
TALKING ABOUT THEM.
- WHATEVER, I COULD TAKE THEM.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT THE...
- LOOK ABOVE US.
- Natsu: AN AIRSHIP?
- MOVE IT OR YOU'LL BE
LEFT BEHIND.
- IT'S THE ROYAL ARMY AGAIN.
- WE GOTTA HIDE.
- Male: I HEARD THEY'RE GONNA
PULL THE MAGIC OUT
OF THAT HUGE LACRIMA,
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW.
- SO, THAT'S WHY THEY'RE CALLING
FOR ADDITIONAL SECURITY DETAIL.
- YEAH, THIS IS BIG
TIME, YOU GUYS.
WE'D BETTER GET ON BOARD.
- THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT OUR FRIENDS.
- AND EVERYBODY
FROM MAGNOLIA, TOO.
- THE MAGIC EXTRACTION
IS IN TWO DAYS?
THAT MEANS IF WE GO ON FOOT,
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
- AND ONCE THE EXTRACTION
PROCESS IS UNDERWAY,
WE'LL LOSE ANY CHANCE
OF TURNING EVERYONE BACK
TO THEIR NORMAL STATES.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO STEAL THAT SHIP.
- STEAL IT? ALL BY OURSELVES?
- THAT'S A COMPLETELY
UNNECESSARY TACTIC.
IT WOULD BE EASIER
TO SIMPLY SNEAK ABOARD.
- MAN, I CAN'T STAND HIDING.
- THIS MUST BE THE WEIRD NATSU,
'CAUSE OURS WOULD NEVER
WANNA RIDE IN A VEHICLE.
- ( chuckles ) THAT'S TRUE,
BUT WITH WENDY'S TROIA SPELL,
VEHICLES AREN'T
A PROBLEM ANYMORE!
- DID YOU REALLY FORGET
THAT WE CAN'T USE MAGIC HERE?
- YOU'RE RIGHT, LET'S FIND
ANOTHER WAY. - IT'S TOO LATE.
- I SAY WE TAKE IT BY FORCE.
IT'S OUR BEST CHANCE OF MAKING
IT IN TIME TO SAVE THEM.
- BUT HOW WILL WE DO THAT?
- DUH, WE'LL USE MY MAGIC.
- DID YOU FORGET YOU'RE
IN THE PRESENCE
OF THE MOST POWERFUL
WIZARD IN FAIRY TAIL?
AND DID YOU NOTICE HOW QUICKLY
WE GOT THE UPPER HAND
ON THOSE SOLDIERS IN LOUEN?
EARTHLAND MAGIC MUST BE
FAR MORE ADVANCED
THAN ANYTHING IN EDOLAS.
- Wendy: YEAH, YOU MAY BE
ON TO SOMETHING.
- CHECK THIS OUT, YOU GUYS.
- YEAH.
- OPEN, GATE OF THE LION, LOKE!
WHAT? VIRGO?
- PLEASE FORGIVE
THIS INTRUSION, PRINCESS.
- WHY'D SHE USE HER?
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
AND WHERE'S LOKE?
- BIG BROTHER IS CURRENTLY
OCCUPIED WITH A DATE.
- HE CANNOT BE SUMMONED
AT THE MOMENT.
- UM, "BIG BROTHER"?
- YES. MASTER LEO REQUESTED THAT
I REFER TO HIM IN THAT MANNER.
- HAS HE LOST EVERY OUNCE
OF SANITY HE HAD?
- THAT'S LUCY FROM FAIRY TAIL!
- CAPTURE HER.
- NOW WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
I WAS COUNTING ON LOKE
TO TAKE ALL OF THEM OUT
AND MAKE ME LOOK
LIKE A POWERHOUSE.
- PRINCESS, IF YOU'LL ALLOW ME,
I BELIEVE I CAN
FULFILL THAT ROLE.
- WITH THE POWER OF
INTERPRETATIVE DANCE. - GO HOME!
- ( grunts )
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST USE
AQUARIUS LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO?
- I CAN'T DO THAT WITHOUT WATER!
- COW MAN.
- THAT WON'T WORK EITHER.
WE'RE GONNA DIE.
- IF OUR MAGIC'S USELESS
WE'LL JUST USE EDOLAS' MAGIC.
- WATCH OUT, BECAUSE WE KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING NOW.
- THAT'S THE STUFF
FROM THE BLACK MARKET.
- ( screams )
- WITHOUT THEIR OWN POWER,
THEY'RE TOTALLY USELESS.
BUT THEY'RE STILL
BETTER THAN LUCY.
- ( sobs ) I WANNA SHINE.
- THE AIRSHIP IS GETTING AWAY.
- WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING QUICK,
OR WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
- GET BACK HERE!
- ( gasps )
- ( screams ) NO.
- ( grunts )
- WHAT IS THAT?
- ( tires screeching )
- WHO'S DRIVING
THE MAGIC MOBILE?
- I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S GOT
FAIRY TAIL'S EMBLEM ON IT.
- LUCY, THOUGHT YOU GUYS
MIGHT NEED A LIFT. HOP IN.
- ( cheers )
- FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELTS, KIDS.
WE'RE RIDING HARD.
GO FIRE!
- SO TO SUMMARIZE,
YOU WERE SENT TO THIS WORLD
BY ONE "MR. MYSTOGAN",
WITH NOTHING BUT A
SIMPLE EXPLANATION
AND THE SHIRT
ON YOUR BACK?
- THAT COULD SUM UP MY ENTIRE
LIFE UP TO THIS POINT.
GETTING USED TO THIS PLACE
AIN'T NO PICNIC,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
- MM, HMM. THIS HAS GOTTA
BE THE MOST BIZARRE STORY
OF MY CAREER.
- WELL, DUH. HOW OFTEN
YOU MEET YOURSELF IN BAR?
- I MUST SAY, YOUR
'SIMPLE' PERSPECTIVE
IS CERTAINLY REFRESHING.
- SEEMS LIKE YOU MADE
QUITE A NAME FOR YOURSELF
AS A MUCKRAKER AROUND HERE.
- INDEED.
INVESTIGATIVE REPORTING
IS MY LIFE'S TRUE CALLING.
SEEKING OUT TRUTH
AND ENLIGHTENING THE MASSES.
- TRUTH AIN'T AN EASY PILL.
BET YOU GOT SOME HATERS.
IN FACT, THERE'RE A FEW LOSERS
THAT ARE MUNCHING DIRT
BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT I WAS YOU.
- WHILE I THANK YOU FOR TAKING
CARE OF SUCH ANNOYANCES FOR ME,
I APOLOGIZE FOR
THE INCONVENIENCE.
TRUTH BE KNOWN, I'VE BECOME
A THORN IN THE SIDE
OF MANY POWERFUL
ORGANIZATIONS.
MY ARTICLES HAVE CAUSED
NUMEROUS PROBLEMS
FOR THE KING AND THE GOVERNMENT
OVER THE YEARS.
YEAH. AS LONG AS I CAN PUT PEN
TO PAD, I WILL WRITE THE TRUTH.
- YOU KNOW, WHEN I HEARD
ABOUT THIS PLACE,
I THOUGHT IT'D BE COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT FROM MY WORLD.
- Both: BUT ME AND YOU
ARE ALMOST EXACTLY ALIKE.
- YOU NOT ONLY DON'T TAKE CRAP
AND FIGHT THE MAN,
BUT YOU DRESS GOOD
AND WRITE FANCY WORDS
LIKE I'D DO IF I CARED.
- AND YOUR UNKEMPT WILDNESS
IS REFLECTIVE OF MY SOUL.
WE HAVE SO MUCH
IN COMMON, MR. ME.
INCIDENTALLY, I'M QUITE SKILLED
WHEN IT COMES
TO PLAYING INSTRUMENTS
AND SINGING.
- OH, ME TOO.
WE'RE A MUSICAL GENIUS.
SOME PALS OF MINE ARE HERE, TOO.
HONESTLY, THEY'RE A
BUNCH OF MORONS.
BUT THEY GOT IT WHERE
IT COUNTS,
AND I'LL BE CAUSING TROUBLE
SOON. WHEN THEY DO...
- YES. I'LL LET YOU KNOW
THE MOMENT THEY STRIKE.
I'VE GOT CONTACTS EVERYWHERE.
THE KING CAN'T SCRATCH HIS NOSE
WITHOUT ME KNOWING ABOUT IT,
SO KEEPING TABS ON THEM
WILL BE EASY.
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
I'LL LIE LOW, TILL YOU
GIVE ME THE WORD.
- WELL, UNTIL THEN.
- DON'T KEEP ME WAITING.
- WE MADE A CLEAN GET AWAY
AND NOW WE GET TO CRUISE
RIGHT ACROSS THE DESERT.
- THANKS A LOT FOR THE RIDE.
- YEAH, YOU JUST
SAVED OUR LIVES.
- NO PROBLEM. MY PLEASURE.
MY WHEELS ARE WAY FASTER
THAN THAT PIECE OF JUNK AIRSHIP.
HA! THEN AGAIN,
THERE ISN'T A VEHICLE
I COULDN'T LEAVE IN THE DUST.
I'M KIND OF A BIG DEAL AROUND
HERE. THEY CALL METHE FIREBALL.
- All: NATSU?
- HUH? IT'S ME?
- THIS IS CRAZY. I MEAN, YOU'RE
NOTHING LIKE THE NATSU WE KNOW.
- AND YOU'RE NOTHING
LIKE MY LUCY.
EXCEPT FOR THE LOOKS, OF COURSE.
SO, IS PUKE- FACE BACK THERE
YOUR 'ME'? TALK ABOUT PATHETIC.
- ( groans )
- HE'S USUALLY NOT LIKE THIS.
HE'S JUST NOT VERY
GOOD WITH VEHICLES.
- JUST DON'T RUIN
THE UPHOLSTERY, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN'T IMAGINE.
THEY WOULDN'T CALL ME "FIREBALL
THE COURIER- WIZARD",
IF I TOSSED MY COOKIES
JUST FROM SITTING IN A CAR.
- ( wretches )
- HOW ARE YOU ABLE TO DRIVE
THIS THING
WITHOUT AN SE PLUG
ATTACHED TO YOUR ARM?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THE SE STANDS FOR
"SELF- ENERGY".
- IT CONVERTS
MAGIC POWER INTO FUEL,
SO WITHOUT ONE,
IT SHOULDN'T RUN AT ALL.
- THEN AGAIN, I GUESS SINCE
PEOPLE IN EDOLAS
DON'T HAVE NATURAL MAGIC POWER,
THEY DON'T NEED SE PLUGS
IN THEIR VEHICLES.
- DOES THAT MEAN THIS THING IS
RUNNING ON ANOTHER POWER SOURCE?
- FASCINATING. THOUGH THEY'RE
LACKING IN MAGICAL PROWESS,
EDOLAS HAS MADE GREAT STRIDES
WHEN IT COMES TO VEHICLES.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( screams )
- ARE YOU TRYING TO MAKE ME
KISS THE DASHBOARD?
- WOW, YOU PEOPLE SURE ARE
IGNORANT. - HUH?
- SINCE MAGIC POWER
IS A LIMITED RESOURCE,
THAT MEANS THINGS LIKE
MAGIC FUEL ARE EQUALLY LIMITED.
IT'S NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE
TO GET A HOLD OF.
LONG STORY SHORT, I CAN'T
REALLY AFFORD
TO TAKE YOU ANY
FURTHER. SO, GET OUT.
- ( exclaims )
- IF I KEEP BURNING
THROUGH FUEL,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO MAKE IT
BACK TO THE GUILD.
THANKS TO THE FAIRY HUNTER,
THEY HAD TO
CHANGE LOCATIONS
AGAIN, RECENTLY.
- HELLO, SOLID GROUND.
I'VE COME BACK TO LIFE!
- I'LL HAND THIS TO YOUR 'ME'.
HE KNOWS WHEN IT'S TIME TO PICK
UP AND MOVE ON.
NOW THEN, GET OUT.
- ( screaming )
- IF YOU WANNA TAKE ON
THE KINGDOM,
THEN, I WON'T STOP YOU.
JUST DON'T GO DRAGGING
MY FAIRY TAIL INTO IT.
I ONLY HELPED YOU
BECAUSE OF LUCY.
NOT YOU, MY LUCY.
I COULD NEVER TURN HER DOWN
WHEN SHE ASKS FOR SOMETHING,
SO THANK HER FOR YOUR RESCUE.
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING ELSE
TO DO WITH YOU.
FOR ME, DRIVING IS ALL
THAT MATTERS.
- HEY.
- HMM.
- I WANNA TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND.
- NO. YOU GET YOUR
HANDS OFF ME, RIGHT NOW.
- SORRY, BUT I GOT TO HAVE A
NICE HEART TO HEART WITH MYSELF.
- WILL YOU CUT IT OUT.
LET GO OF ME, NO.
I CAN'T GET OUT OF THE CAR.
- NOW TELL ME. WHY IS IT
YOU DON'T GET CAR SICK?
- THAT WAS YOUR BIG BEEF?
- ( whimpers )
- HUH?
- I, I...
- ( sobs ) I DON'T KNOW WHY. I'M
SORRY. PLEASE, DON'T HURT ME.
- All: HUH?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: SO EDOLAS IS WHERE
YOU'RE ORIGINALLY FROM?
DO YOU RECOGNIZE
ANY OF THE PLACES WE'VE BEEN?
- Happy: HOW COULD I?
I WAS STILL AN EGG LAST
TIME I WAS HERE, REMEMBER?
- OH YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WAIT, THEN HOW DOES CARLA KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT THIS PLACE?
- MAYBE SHE GOT A SPECIAL
EDUCATION
FROM A GUY WHO TEACHES EGGS.
- WOW. EDOLAS IS REALLY
AHEAD OF US.
- Both: NEXT TIME, WELCOME HOME.
- Happy: I MAY BE FROM EDOLAS,
BUT EARTHLAND'S FAIRY TAIL
IS MY ONE, TRUE HOME.
- Natsu: YEAH, TOOK THE WORDS
RIGHT OUT OF MY MOUTH.
- Happy: OH, COULD YOU
PUT A FISH INTO MINE?