Have you learned your lesson,
or should I keep beating it in?
I'm fine with that.
Remember this the next time
[MINERVA]
you think of defying me!
Stop the match, now!
We can't lose the
Celestial wizard!
Call it off,
before it's too late!
[bell dinging]
[CHAPATI] The referee
has stopped the fight!
The Naval Battle is over!
Sabertooth takes
first place with
an overwhelming
show of brutal force!
It doesn't look
like Lucy is moving.
Can we please get the
paramedics on the field?
[GRAY and NATSU] Lucy!
[GRAY and NATSU grunt]
Come on, Lucy!
Please say something!
What in the
hell is your problem?
You went way too far!
Take the Celestial wizard
to the infirmary at once!
Hold on! I need to give her
special emergency treatment!
I'll help you!
Just hang in there, Lucy!
What a scornful expression.
Here we go!
She's hurt pretty bad,
so let's combine our powers.
You can glare at
me all you want,
if it makes you feel better.
But remember that I
acted in full compliance
with the rules
of the competition.
That may be true...
but you went way
outside the bounds
of basic human decency.
[chuckles]
I was simply trying to
entertain the crowd, that's all.
To be quite honest,
you should be thanking me.
She got second
place, didn't she?
[MINNERVA] She could never
have done that without my help.
What?
What is going
on down there?
Both teams are on the
ground and ready to rumble!
[MALE 172A]
Sweet bonus round action!
[MALE 172B] Sabertooth
versus Fairy Tail!
They're both
hot-tempered guilds,
but they need to
play it cool right now.
The dramatic tension in the
air is absolutely delicious!
Thank you very much!
Yeah. Well, I guess
we shoulda seen this one
comin' from a mile away.
It was bound to
happen, alright.
Since this isn't a
part of the contest.
We should be ready to go down
there and lend them a hand.
Aye, Sir!
Would you tomcats
please calm down?
That's how we like it!
[NOVALI, SEMUS,
and YAEGAR] Wild!
[MATO] This is most certainly
a thrilling turn of events!
Do we join them?
I don't know.
Man.
[CROWD chanting "fight"]
Although you may be considered
the strongest guild in Fiore,
you'd be wise to
heed this warning.
[ERZA] Listen carefully.
Making an enemy of
Fairy Tail is a decision
that you will regret.
[HAPPY] A Parfum for You!
She's gonna be okay,
isn't she?
Any word on
Lucy's condition?
Is she awake?
You guys came!
We may be on
different teams,
but we're all in the same guild.
Laxus?
So, how is she?
She's not out of the woods yet,
but she'll pull
through thanks to Wendy.
No, it wasn't just me,
we're lucky Shelia
was there to help out, too.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad to hear
she hasn't sustained
any lasting injuries.
They're gonna pay.
You can sure as
hell bet on that one.
She's awake!
You guys. I'm sorry.
Say what?
Why are you apologizing?
[LUCY] Because
I screwed up again.
Are you kidding?
Second place is nothing
to be sorry about.
We got eight
points in that round!
Yes. Good job!
But, I lost my keys.
[HAPPY] I've got 'em right here.
Oh that's a relief.
Thank you, Happy.
I think she's
gonna be okay.
But we still
can't let those guys
get away with this kinda crap.
I feel the exact same way.
Lousy buncha scumbags.
[door opens]
Master!
Unfortunate circumstances, but
I'm glad both teams are here.
I have something to tell you.
I was just contacted
by the games' organizers,
though I'm not sure if we'll
be a help or hindrance to us,
we've been asked to consolidate
our two teams into one.
Say what?
So we gotta be like
everybody else now, huh?
Why are they doing that?
[MAKAROV] Since Raven
Tail has been disqualified,
there are now seven
teams remaining.
Having an odd number
makes it difficult
to match up competitors
for the battles.
Therefore, we've
been ordered to do away
with the A and B
groups and form a single
five-person team for the
rest of the tournament.
So, we're losing
five members.
But how will this
affect our scores?
Mm.
We're only allowed to
keep the lower one.
And that would be the
thirty-five points from Team A.
But that's totally unfair!
Fair or not,
the decision's been made,
so we'd better accept it.
Look on the bright side,
this just means we're gonna
be able to put together
an even more kick-ass team.
Well, I wish this woulda
happened a little bit earlier.
Because the only
thing we have left now
are two man
battles, right?
You're wrong.
Traditionally, there
is a mandatory day off.
Followed by a battle
involving all members.
It's important to
choose carefully.
No matter what happens,
I'm gonna get revenge for Lucy!
If they think they
can treat her like that,
I'll show 'em myself
that they're dead wrong!
Day four's battle round
is about to be underway.
And we'll soon find out who
made the cut on team Fairy Tail!
You have a long history
with the guild, Mr. Yajima.
Got any predictions
on the final five?
No comment.
[CHAPATI] And once again,
joining us is Mr. Lavian,
noted thespian and founder
of the Scheherazade theatre.
[LAVIAN] Thank you very much
for this wonderful opportunity!
But don't forget,
today's team matches
are no mere stage combat.
That may be true,
but they still require
a certain kind of choreography
in their own right!
Let's get down to
business and announce
the lineups for
today's battles!
[CHAPATI] Now. Please turn your
attention to the lacrima-trons!
Match one will be
Blue Pegasus versus
the frisky Quattro Puppy!
[CHAPATI] Then on to round two,
the ladies of Mermaid Heel
facing off against Lamia Scale!
And then what could
be today's highlight,
Sabertooth against
the new Fairy Tail!
[cheering]
[CHAPATI] So put your
hands together for a big
Domus Flau welcome, and let's
meet the Fairy Tail team!
Go get 'em, guys. For me.
We're all countin' on ya.
Master really did put
together an amazing team.
Show 'em what
you're made of!
Bring home a win!
It's just like I
was saying before!
This team will surely get
us back to number one again!
Mmmmmm.
The spirit of our guild is
a truly unstoppable force.
[MAKAROV] And these five kids
embody that spirit
wholeheartedly!
It's time to show
the entire world
the real power our
friendship can wield.
[cheering]
We've been waiting
for this moment!
[CHAPATI] It's my
pleasure to introduce...
[CHAPATI]
The new Team Fairy Tail!
[CROWD cheering]
♪
With that kind of
entrance, I'm not sure
the audience will be able
to handle the anticipation
leading up to
today's final match!
The fans are looking forward
to it, that's for sure.
I'm thankful I get
to be part of a day
filled with such drama!
[screaming and cheering]
The Celestial wizard
isn't with them?
I would assume
she's still recovering.
Listen. You'd better
not try anything
as foolish as last time.
[ARCADIOS] Perish the thought.
I'll be the first to
admit that was a misstep.
I intend to take more reliable
measures from here on out.
[DARTON sighs]
[ARCADIOS] For now,
let us enjoy the festival.
The project will commence
in three days' time.
That damned Eclipse.
And then the world
will be forever changed.
[DARTON] Is there no way
we can put a stop to it?
We can't let Zeref
wait much longer, can we?
[chuckles]
♪
I'm all fired up now.
[DARTON] The Grand Magic Games.
[DARTON]
Those who know history...
know that long ago,
they went by another name.
[DARTON]
The Dragon King Festival.
A feast of dragons,
men, and sorcery.
[CHAPATI] Aright people! Are
you ready for a magic battle?
[cheering]
[CHAPATI] First up... Blue
Pegasus' Ichiya and Rabbit...
versus Quattro Puppy's
Bacchus and Rocker!
[hiccups]
Watch out, we're...
[ALL] Wild!
Now let's show
these fancy boys
what that really means.
We gotta get some points too.
It's cool.
All I want is to get my spirit
shaken and stirred! Huh?
Eh-uhh!
[ICHIYA] Sirs?
[BACCHUS and ROCKER] Uhhh...
[CHAPATI] Wow.
After all the animosity
of today's Naval Battle.
These fine gentlemen are
putting civility on display.
[LAVIAN] What a beautiful
gesture! Thank you very much!
[ROCKER] Did I just
shake hands with a bunny?
[BACCHUS] Ya know, that guy
smells pretty damn good.
Now, the time has
come to share your
handsome face with the world!
Seriously?
We're finally gonna
find out who he is?
[gasping]
It's so strange, but all
the suspense is killing me.
Who's in there?
Would you two stop
for just a second?
[EVE] Ichiya's just about to
show us who's in the bunny suit!
Obscure yourself no more.
Unmask your true glory.
[CROWD] Huh?
[ALL] Aaah...
[ALL] What?
[BACCHUS and ROCKER] Uh, whoa!
Holy crap!
That cat from Extalia!
[BOTH] Ready?
Double Studmuffin Attack!
[MALE 172C] Eww, yuck!
[MALE 172D] What is that thing?
It's Nichiya!
Huh?
Sensual.
Yet, deadly parfum.
[ALL] Uh?
[ALL] Ughhh...
[groans]
Can it be true?
[BOTH] Ready?
Double Studmuffin Attack!
I don't feel so good.
Pull yourself together!
That is so totally not wild!
I mean, is that
crazy-looking cat-dude
even really a member
of Blue Pegasus?
[ICHIYA chuckles]
Behold!
[NICHIYA meows]
[CROWD] Whoa!
Of course, I made that
darling little pussycat
an official member of
our guild well before
the Grand Magic Games began!
Honestly, he's such a
handsome creature it would be
practically criminal to
turn him away, you know? Oh!
But how did Blue
Pegasus even find him
in the first place?
Hm. 'Twas a stroke
of true destiny.
A fate written in
the stars themselves.
Yes, though it happened
one sunny afternoon.
[ICHIYA] With an intoxicating
parfum of new experience
hanging heavily in the air,
I ventured into the forest.
I went in deep, but my
search remained fruitless.
I asked myself this question...
"Is this the parfum
of lost souls, man?"
I attempted to leave,
but only found myself
getting even deeper inside.
Ravenous and thirsty,
I collapsed to the ground.
[meowing]
[ICHIYA] But fortune
smiled on me that day.
For as it turns out,
this forest was home to
Exceeds who had
come to Earth Land.
[NICHIYA] What an
incredibly handsome human!
[ICHIYA] What an
incredibly handsome cat!
Hi. Lost?
Uh-huh.
Is there some way
I can help you?
Water, please.
Mm. Of course.
Ooh...
A fine idea indeed.
[ICHIYA] Surprisingly,
this development was rich
with the parfum of a
classic romantic drama!
Pardon me.
[laughs] That
perked me up, man!
Glad to be of help, man!
Man.
[ICHIYA] My nostrils
sing with the parfum
of flowering friendship!
[NICHIYA] Feel free to
remain in this forest with me
until you've
regained your sparkle!
And thus, as I predicted,
the seed planted
that day blossomed
into a beautiful pairing.
And we drink deep
the parfum of memory.
[grunts]
--[BACCHUS] Ya!
--[NICHIYA] Man!
No!
Man!
What happened?
Can the cat even fight?
Of course he can!
The feline and I
are one and the same!
[ICHIYA] Which means...
we should both share
the same abilities!
[groans]
He's completely
out of commission!
What a tragedy!
[BACCHUS and ROCKER] Wild.
Let's get this over with.
This victory couldn't
have come at a better time.
We gotta get some
points on the board.
[CHAPATI] It looks
like it's rabbit season
here in Domus Flau!
It's two against one now.
So tragic and yet so thrilling!
[LAVIAN] Thank you very much!
Please, hold on just one moment!
Drillin' Rock For Ya!
Drunken Chop-Hanging
Palm, Under Moon!
[ICHIYA] Man!
Ichiya.
Nichiya.
Last call, fancy boy!
Time to eat some dirt!
[ICHIYA] I'm sorry I dragged you
into this battle. My mistake.
I should've known that
you're a lover, not a fighter.
Drillin Rock For ya! Bam!
[ICHIYA] Man!
[ICHIYA] And yet...
you chose the noble path
and fought bravely.
[ICHIYA] You put your
handsome face in harm's way.
I've failed my most
beautiful friend!
How could I have let you fall?
[groans]
[CHAPATI] Is that it? Did
Bacchus deal the final blow?
Now Ichiya joins
his furry teammate
on the floor of the arena,
and it's not looking
good for Blue Pegasus.
[BOTH] What are we, boys?
[ALL] Wild!
[CHAPATI] Wait! It's not over
yet! Ichiya appears to be
slowly getting up!
Will he be able to stand?
[ICHIYA] I swear to you...
I won't let your
struggle be in vain!
[ICHIYA] I will reveal the
handsome face of justice!
[ICHIYA yells]
Muscle, muscle! Man!
Man, man, muscle, muscle!
Muscle, man, man!
What the hell is this?
How did he get so wild?
Maybe it's power potion?
To my dear friend. I dedicate
the parfum of victory!
[All] Go get 'em!
[grunts]
[MATO] This is great!
I never expected this fight
would be so emotional.
[BACCHUS AND ROCKER]
Let's get wild!
Here I come with some
Drillin' Rock For Ya!
My soul is shaken and stirred!
Drunken Chop-Hanging Palm!
Give it your all.
But your attacks will melt...
against my Beautiful Dreamer!
[ICHIYA] Smile!
[BOTH] Huh?
And smash!
[gasps and groans]
[ALL] Uh...!
[CHAPATI] And from that
devastating charm offensive,
Quattro Puppy is down!
The winner is Blue Pegasus!
[ICHIYA] Man!
[CROWD cheering]
He actually took down Bacchus?
Both him and his buddy. Man.
[GRAY] I guess he's
not just an idiot.
[NATSU] He's totally awesome!
Talk about a
stud-muffin. He rules.
Ichiya's the man, for sure.
What a hunk!
[EVE] I wanna be just like him!
Are you alright... my friend?
Man, my pride hurts.
[CHAPATI] That was an amazing
match, don't you think?
Sure. If you say so.
[LAVIAN] The ending was
far too sappy for my taste,
thank you very much.
[CHAPATI] And we're diving
straight into round two
which puts Lamia
Scale's Lyon and Yuka...
[CROWD cheers]
[CHAPATI] against Mermaid
Heel's top dog Kagura,
and top cat Millianna!
[CROWD cheers]
Lyon and Kagura are fighting?
This is gonna be a good one.
[growls]
[HAPPY] And joining me today
is guest commentator, Natsu.
Tell me, what are your
thoughts on this matchup?
[NATSU] Lyon doesn't like Gray,
so he can't be all that bad.
And Yuka is the
eyebrow dude from Galuna
with the wavy magic, right?
[HAPPY] Uh-huh.
[NATSU] Now Kagura,
naw, I got nothin'!
And I bet if you
dress like a cat,
Milliana will hug ya to death!
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
"Battle of Dragon Slayers!"
[HAPPY] Thank you, Natsu. You
shared with our viewers at home
your total lack of insight.
[NATSU] Ha-ha! That's what I do!