- Kain: WE LANDED
ON THIS FREAKY LOOKIN' ISLAND
TO CARRY OUT TWO CRITICAL
MISSIONS FOR OUR MASTER.
( panting )
THE FIRST ONE IS TO CAPTURE THE
LEGENDARY BLACK WIZARD ZEREF,
ALIVE AND UNHARMED.
THE SECOND ONE IS...
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?
OH, RIGHT.
I'M ALL ALONE IN THIS PLACE.
WHERE DID EVERYONE GO?
I THINK... I'M LOST!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
UNTIL THE COUNT OF THE THREE
TO GET OUT OF MY SIGHT,
OTHERWISE YOU AND YOUR COMRADES
WILL SEE THE OTHER SIDE
OF OBLIVION.
- THE ULTIMATE MAGIC SPELL
THAT VANQUISHES EVERYONE
WHOM THE CASTER
DEEMS TO BE A FOE...
- ONE!
- LET'S SEE YOUR FAIRY LAW
IN ACTION.
- TWO!
AND THAT'S THREE.
TIME'S UP!
FAIRY... LAW!
- DON'T BE SO HASTY.
GRIMOIRE...
LAW.
- ( grunts )
WHAT? IMPOSSIBLE!
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
- HELLO, BOY.
YOU'RE LOOKING WELL.
- IT IS YOU.
MASTER PRECHT!
- ( growls )
DAMN IT! WHO DO THOSE COUNCIL
LOW-LIFES THINK THEY ARE?!
I'VE HALF A MIND TO SQUASH
'EM INTO THE GROUND!
- OH, YOU WANT ME
TO CALM DOWN?
MAYBE I'LL USE YOU TO VENT
THESE PENT-UP FRUSTRATIONS!
- WAIT!
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS!
- Precht: THAT'S ENOUGH, BOY.
LET HIM GO.
- OH, MASTER!
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE BACK.
- DO YOU REVEL IN MAKING TROUBLE
WHENEVER YOU GO ON A JOB?!
- Makarov: SO I ROUGHED UP
SOME HAS-BEEN BANDITS
WHO WERE TALKIN' SMACK
ABOUT OUR GUILD.
I DON'T SEE
WHAT THE PROBLEM IS.
- THERE IS NOTHING WRONG
WITH FEELING THE NEED
TO DEFEND SOMETHING
YOU HOLD SO DEAR.
BUT VIOLENCE ULTIMATELY
BEGETS MORE VIOLENCE.
- WAS I JUST SUPPOSED
TO LET 'EM GET AWAY WITH IT?
- HARMONY IS KEY.
FORGIVENESS CAN BE
A POWERFUL THING,
JUST LIKE VIOLENCE.
WHETHER YOU FORGIVE
OR SEEK REVENGE
IS UP TO YOU.
BUT KNOW THE CONSEQUENCES.
- YOU EVER GET TIRED
OF SAYIN' THAT?
- I'LL KEEP SAYING IT
UNTIL IT SINKS
INTO YOUR THICK SKULL, BOY.
- SERIOUSLY!
STOP CALLING ME "BOY!"
- MASTER.
IT'S REALLY YOU.
WHY?
IS THIS SOME SICK JOKE?
( grunting )
( growls )
I SEE YOU'VE TRADED IN
YOUR IDEALS FOR A DARKER ROBE.
- AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
YOU STILL VIEW THE WORLD
IN BLACK AND WHITE.
I'D HOPED BECOMING
GUILD MASTER
WOULD BROADEN
THAT NARROW VIEW OF YOURS.
- FORGIVE ME IF I DON'T
GIVE A DAMN.
I MAY HAVE A NARROW
FIELD OF VISION,
BUT I SEE
MY ENEMIES CLEARLY.
- ( laughs )
AT LEAST YOU LEARNED
HOW TO TALK THE TALK
WHILE I'VE BEEN AWAY, BOY.
- I ALWAYS HATED
THAT NICKNAME.
IN FACT, I WANTED TO DECK YOU
EVERY TIME YOU USED IT.
BUT I HAVE NO DESIRE
TO FIGHT YOU NOW.
LEAVE BEFORE WE DO
SOMETHING DRASTIC.
- THOUGH IT PAINS ME
TO DO SO,
MY PATH IS ALL TOO CLEAR
AT THIS POINT.
IT WOULD SEEM
FATE HAS CHOSEN ME
AS THE INSTRUMENT
OF FAIRY TAIL'S DESTRUCTION.
- BUT FIRST, YOU'LL HAVE
TO GO THROUGH ME!
- IF YOU WISH TO THROW
YOUR LIFE AWAY, BOY,
SO BE IT.
- PURGE THE DARKNESS,
O RAIN OF LIGHT!
- THAT WON'T BE ENOUGH.
MAKAROV.
SWALLOW THE LIGHT,
O SHADOW
OF ETERNAL DARKNESS!
- IN THAT CASE!
WHAT?!
HE CAST AN AMATERASU
FORMULA 28 CIRCLE
AS IF IT WERE NOTHING.
- UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU'RE UP AGAINST NOW?
- ( whooshing )
- ( both grunting )
- ( screams )
- I LIVE AND BREATHE
THE DARK ARTS.
YOUR DEFEAT IS CERTAIN.
- ( groaning )
WHAT IS THIS?!
- MMM.
- MAXIMUM DEFENSE
MAGIC CIRCLE.
THREE PILLAR GODS!
- AMATERASU FORMULA 100.
- ( cawing )
- ( screams, grunts )
- I DIDN'T LIKE THE SOUND
OF THAT. - ME EITHER!
I HOPE ONE OF OUR GUYS
CAST THAT THING.
- I'M GETTING REALLY TIRED
OF THESE JERK-WADS
PLAYING IN OUR BACKYARD.
- THERE'S SO MANY OF THEM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEY WANT?
- I DON'T KNOW,
AND TO BE HONEST I DON'T CARE!
EVERY ONE OF THESE
GRIMY HAMBURGERS
ARE ABOUT TO FEEL THE BURN!
- WAIT, AREN'T THEY CALLED
"GRIMOIRE HEART"?
- DON'T BOTHER CORRECTING HIM,
HE'S ON A ROLL!
- ( thinking )
MEST MENTIONED SOMETHING
ABOUT THE LEGENDARY
BLACK WIZARD BEFORE.
COULD IT BE...
GRIMOIRE HEART'S GOAL
IS TO FIND...
- LORD ZEREF.
- YOU'RE GETTING IN MY WAY!
- ( roaring )
- WIND BLADE!
- HOLY CRAP!
SHE'S PISSED!
SHE DESTROYED THOSE GUYS!
- TOO BAD. IT'S THEIR FAULT.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE TRESPASSIN'
ON SACRED GROUND.
- HEAR THAT?
HOPE YOU'RE READY FOR MORE!
- ( roars )
- ( gasps )
- CANA!
STAY FOCUSED, WOULD YA?!
- YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
THANKS, LUCY.
- C'MON.
THERE'S NO END TO 'EM!
THEY CRAWLIN' OUT
OF THE GROUND TOO?
- THERE MAY BE A LOT,
BUT THEY'RE PRETTY WEAK OVERALL.
- THAT DOESN'T HELP IF
THE ATTACKS NEVER STOP COMING.
- Cana: SHE'S RIGHT. WE CAN'T
KEEP THIS UP INDEFINITELY.
WITH THESE NUMBERS,
THEY'LL EVENTUALLY WEAR US OUT.
ONCE WE'VE EXHAUSTED
OUR MAGIC POWER,
THEY CAN PICK US OFF WITH EASE.
- IF I SUMMON TAURUS
OR SAGITTARIUS
WE MIGHT EVEN THE ODDS.
- THAT'S TOO MUCH OF A GAMBLE.
IF THEY HAVE MORE REINFORCEMENTS
YOU'D JUST BE WASTING POWER.
- NOW I'M MAD!
AND IF THEY THINK
THEY CAN TAKE US
WITH A BUNCH OF MASK-WEARIN'
CLOWNS, THEY'RE DEAD WRONG.
- ( grunts )
- ( groans )
- WATER LOCK!
- NOT GOOD.
NUMBERS DON'T SEEM TO BE
DECREASING AT ALL, DO THEY?
- THAT EXPLOSION. DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT CAUSED IT?
IT GAVE OFF TREMENDOUS
MAGIC POWER.
- I KNOW.
WE CAN WORRY ABOUT THAT
AFTER WE'VE DEALT WITH THE
PROBLEM AT HAND. - RIGHT.
OH, GRAY, ALTHOUGH
THE ENEMY SURROUNDS ME,
I CAN ONLY THINK
OF YOUR GORGEOUS FACE.
WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE TO BE
FIGHTING BY YOUR SIDE
INSTEAD OF ERZA'S!
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HANDLE THEM ON YOUR OWN?!
- NO, MA'AM!
- ( screaming )
- GO, DREAM KNOCK!
- ( sighs )
- THIS KITTEN'S GOT CLAWS!
MEOW!
- ( groans )
- ARE YOU OKAY, LISANNA?
- I'M FINE.
YOU THINK THE OTHERS HAVE
RUN INTO THE SAME PROBLEM?
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
JUST KEEP DEFENDING THE CAMP!
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- MANLY STRIKE!
EVERGREEN, TIME TO DO
YOUR THING!
- I'LL SAY THIS AGAIN:
WHEN I NEED A BIG OAF
TO ORDER ME AROUND,
YOU'LL BE THE FIRST TO KNOW!
- WHAT THE--
- I CAN'T MOVE!
- DON'T LOOK INTO HER EYES!
- SHE'S USING
PETRIFICATION MAGIC!
- WELL, NORMALLY I WOULDN'T
RESORT TO SUCH CHEAP TACTICS,
BUT IF IT GETS THE JOB DONE,
I GUESS IT'S MANLY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "CHEAP"?!
- ( thinking )
THE FIGHTING NEVER ENDS.
NOTHING EVER CHANGES.
IS IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR EXISTENCE
TO MOVE FORWARD
WITHOUT VIOLENCE?
IS IT SO INTRINSIC?
WHAT WILL IT TAKE TO END
THE CONFLICT OCCURRING NOW?
CAN THERE EVER BE PEACE?
OR IS DEATH THE ONLY WAY?
- ( soft moans )
- I'D EXPECT NO LESS
FROM MY SUCCESSOR.
IT'S NO SURPRISE YOU'VE HELD
THE GUILD TOGETHER
FOR 48 YEARS.
- ( groaning )
- HMM?
WHAT IS IT, BOY?
ARE YOU NOT FEELING WELL?
I GUESS THE YEARS ARE
CATCHING UP WITH YOU.
NEARLY HALF A CENTURY
HAS PASSED
SINCE WE PARTED WAYS.
DOES FATE INTEND
TO BRING US FULL CIRCLE ON THIS
LONELY AND VENERATED GROUND?
- ( grunts )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
YOU WERE AN AMAZING
GUILD MASTER, PRECHT.
YOU ALWAYS SPOKE OF HARMONY
AND DID YOUR BEST TO LEAD US
TOWARD A PATH OF RIGHTEOUSNESS.
DID YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND
OR WAS IT ALL A LIE?
( moans )
- LONG AGO, MAGIC WAS BORN
FROM THE DEPTHS OF DARKNESS.
AND THOSE WHO
UTILIZED ITS POWER
WERE MET WITH FEAR
AND PREJUDICE.
EVENTUALLY MAGIC
BECAME COMMONPLACE,
SO MUCH THAT WE INTEGRATED IT
INTO OUR CULTURE.
BUT AS I DELVED DEEPER
INTO THE SOURCE OF MAGIC,
I FOUND THAT IT ALWAYS
LEAD BACK TO ZEREF.
AT LAST I SAW THE TRUTH.
I HAD FOUND THE PERSONIFICATION
OF WIZARDRY.
SLEEP, BOY.
FAIRY TAIL SHALL REST HERE,
WITH MAVIS.
- ( growling )
( screaming )
- IT'S NOT OVER.
NOT YET.
MY SUCCESSOR,
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
TO BEAR THIS BURDEN.
- HUH?
I FEEL LIKE
SOMEONE JUST
WALKED OVER MY GRAVE.
- ( screaming )
- YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA CATCH ME!
- STUPID FLYING CAT!
- WE'VE GOT YOU NOW!
- ( yelps )
WHATEVER WILL I DO?!
YOU TOTALLY FELL FOR IT.
- All: NO NO NO NO NO!
- ( giggles )
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- LILY!
- DON'T OVERDO IT!
JUST SAVE YOUR STRENGTH!
- DAMN.
IF I HAD MORE MAGIC POWER
I COULD HELP NATSU
AND HAPPY FIGHT THEM OFF.
- YOU'LL HAVE
TO SIT THIS ONE OUT.
WENDY CAN HEAL BUT SHE CAN'T
RESTORE YOUR POWER.
LET THEM HANDLE THIS.
- WE'RE IN A CRISIS
AND I'M STUCK ON THE SIDELINES?
UTTERLY DISGRACEFUL!
- DID YOU SEE
WHERE MEST WENT OFF TO?
- FORGET HIM.
WORRY ABOUT YOURSELF, CHILD.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
YOU SHOULD HURRY
AND USE YOUR MAGIC
TO HEAL THOSE WOUNDS.
- THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS.
- I WAS AFRAID
YOU'D SAY THAT.
- YOU GUYS SHOULD HIDE!
- BUT, HAPPY--
- DON'T WORRY, NATSU AND I
CAN HANDLE 'EM, NO PROBLEM!
- VERY WELL.
CAN'T BE HELPED.
SO WE'LL LEAVE IT TO YOU.
BEST OF LUCK.
- YOU'RE SERIOUS?
- IN OUR CURRENT CONDITION
WE'RE A LIABILITY AND WOULD ONLY
BE A BURDEN ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
- DON'T FEEL BAD. YOU CAN KICK
BACK AND TAKE A LOAD OFF.
LEAVE THE WORK TO THE REAL
HEROES OF THE STORY!
- I'VE GOT ENOUGH ENERGY
TO SLAP HIM AROUND A BIT.
- LILY, NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
YOU CAN GIVE HIM A GOOD SMACK
ONCE WE'RE HOME.
- AW, C'MON, DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE DONE ALREADY!
INVADING OUR ISLAND
IS BAD ENOUGH,
BUT MY PRECIOUS SCARF
TURNING BLACK HAS ME
BURNIN' UP WITH ANGER!
LET ME KICK YOUR TEETH IN
A LITTLE BIT MORE!
- WHAT?! YOU'RE JUST VENTING
ON US? - WHAT A JERK!
- WE DIDN'T TOUCH
YOUR SCARF!
- I'LL DO MORE
THAN BURN IT BLACK.
I'LL TURN IT TO ASH!
- HUH?
- FIRE BULLET!
- HEE HEE!
COME TO PAPA!
- ( cheering )
- BULL'S-EYE!
- THAT'S WHAT YOU GET!
- ( laughs )
MY FIRE BULLETS ARE HOT ENOUGH
TO MELT SOLID ROCK.
I DON'T CARE IF HE WAS
A FIRE WIZARD,
HE COULDN'T'VE SURVIVED--
WHAT THE HELL?!
- WHAT IS THIS GUY?
- HE'S EATING FIRE?!
- IMPOSSIBLE!
- WAIT, IS HE...
- AHH. - ...THE ONE
EVERYONE TALKS ABOUT?
- THANKS FOR THE SNACK;
NOW I GOT A FIRE IN MY BELLY!
- THE DRAGON SLAYER.
NATSU THE SALAMANDER?!
- FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
- ( moaning )
- HE'S TOO MUCH FOR US!
- YEAH.
WE SHOULD GET OUTTA HERE!
- NO MATTER WHAT WE THROW
AT THIS MONSTER
WE CAN'T EVEN TOUCH HIM!
- WHO ARE YOU CALLIN'
A MONSTER?
- ( whimpering )
- Zancrow: ENOUGH ALREADY!
( laughs )
I CAN'T WATCH ANYMORE.
( laughing )
- UHH.
- Soldier: IT'S ZANCROW!
- HMM?
- Zancrow: LEAVE HIM TO ME.
I WAS HOPING TO GET SOME
EXERCISE ON THIS TRIP.
HUH, I'LL POUND THIS RUNT
INTO THE DIRT
WHILE YOU GO
LOOK FOR ZEREF.
JUDGING BY WHAT
I'VE SEEN SO FAR,
IT SHOULDN'T TAKE MORE
THAN A FEW MINUTES.
- ZEREF?
- Wendy: SO GRIMOIRE
HEART'S GOAL
REALLY IS THE BLACK WIZARD.
- Pantherlily: AND WE'RE JUST
CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
- Carla: WHY ARE THINGS
ALWAYS SO COMPLICATED?
- THANKS A LOT, ZANCROW!
- WE OWE YOU ONE!
- I DIDN'T THINK THEY
HAD ANYONE THAT STRONG.
- HE DEFINITELY
LIVES UP TO HIS REP.
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- ( wails )
- HE'S STRONG? THIS FAIRY
TAIL PANSY SCARES YOU?!
- UH... WELL.
- IT WAS A SLIP OF THE TONGUE!
- PLEASE FORGIVE US!
- THERE'S NO GUILD IN THIS WORLD
THAT CAN COME CLOSE
TO THE STRENGTH
OF GRIMOIRE HEART, UNDERSTAND?!
- BLACK FLAMES?
- IF YOU THINK
HE'S STRONGER THAN US,
THEN YOU DON'T BELONG HERE!
- DO YOU FEEL THAT POWER?
- I DON'T LIKE
THE LOOKS OF THIS.
- AND AS OF NOW,
YOU'RE ALL OUTTA THE GUILD!
- ( whimpers, screams  )
- NO WAY!
HE JUST WASTED HIS OWN MEN!
- ( cackling )
- YOU JERK!
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT
TO YOUR FRIENDS?!
- THEY WEREN'T MY FRIENDS.
IT'S NOT YOUR BUSINESS ANYWAY.
AND IF I WERE AS WEAK AS YOU,
I'D BE CAREFUL WHO I
RUN MY MOUTH TO!
- WHAT A JOKE! DON'T YOU KNOW
YOUR FIRE AIN'T GONNA HURT ME?!
- NATSU! STAY BACK!
THOSE FLAMES ARE BAD NEWS!
DON'T LET 'EM TOUCH YOU!
- ( moans )
( screams )
( gagging )
WHY CAN'T I EAT IT?!
WHAT IS THIS?!
YOU TRICKED ME!
- THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR BEING SO COCKY!
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE MAIN COURSE!
( cackling )
- NO, NATSU!
- I THOUGHT THAT
A FIRE DRAGON SLAYER
COULD EAT ANY FLAME IN
EXISTENCE! - ( grunting )
- ( laughs )
SERVES YOU RIGHT
FOR TRYING TO EAT
ABOVE YOUR STATURE,
YOU LOWLY DRAGON HUNTER.
D'YOU LIKE MY DIVINE FLAMES?
- WHADDAYA MEAN
"DIVINE" FLAMES?
- EXACTLY WHAT
IT SOUNDS LIKE.
MY MAGIC IS WAY
OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE.
YOU'RE UP AGAINST
A GOD SLAYER.
MAKE PEACE
WITH YOUR OWN, FAST!
- Wendy: A GOD SLAYER?!
- ( all panting )
- NOT GOOD. I'M ALMOST
COMPLETELY OUT OF POWER.
- SAME HERE. BUT I THINK
WE PUT MOST OF 'EM DOWN.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TAKE OUT
THE REST OF 'EM AND GO
LOOK FOR THE OTHERS.
- Lucy: BUT WHAT IF THEY'RE
FIGHTING THESE GUYS TOO?
WE WON'T BE ANY HELP!
- Gray: WE'LL CROSS THAT BRIDGE
WHEN WE COME TO IT,
BUT RIGHT NOW WE GOTTA--
- Loke: WAIT!
I SENSE SOMETHING.
- ( all gasp ) - ARE THEY
TURNING INVISIBLE ON US?!
- MAYBE THEY WERE JUST
SUPPOSED TO DISTRACT US
AND THEY SUCCEEDED.
- OR THEY ALL LEFT...
BECAUSE OF HIM!
- Caprico: THEY'RE INCAPABLE
OF DEFEATING YOU,
SO THERE'S NO NEED FOR THEM
TO CONTINUE FIGHTING.
BUT YOUR FIGHT IS FAR FROM OVER
PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
- THAT'S...
- A GOAT?
WEARING A SUIT?
- ( hisses )
- YOU OKAY THERE?
- YEAH.
BUT KEEP YOUR GUARD UP,
THIS GUY'S ON A WHOLE OTHER
LEVEL THAN HIS FLUNKIES.
WE'RE IN FOR ONE HECK
OF A FIGHT.
- Juvia: HOPEFULLY THAT
WAS THE WORST OF THEM.
- I WOULDN'T COUNT ON IT.
- RIGHT.
- ( chimes )
- WHO GOES THERE?!
- I HAVE ENCOUNTERED
THE ENEMY DURING THE MISSION.
I WILL DESTROY THEM
IMMEDIATELY.
ENDING THEIR LIVES IS NOW
MY HIGHEST PRIORITY.
COMMENCING
COMBAT OPERATIONS.
- A CHILD?
- DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT THIS GIRL.
- ( scoffs ) THAT A BAD GUY
OR A FLOWER ARRANGEMENT?
- WHATEVER IT IS,
IT TOOK A BATH IN COLOGNE.
- ( sighs ) IN A DESOLATE
FOREST ON A LONELY ISLAND,
THE DEVILS AND FAIRIES
DANCED A TANGO OF DEATH.
- UH...
- I AIN'T DANCING.
- UH-HA.
MAY THESE STONES AND MOSS
SERVE AS A BALLROOM
FOR OUR SOIREE.
- Elfman: CAN I PUNCH HIM NOW?
- IF IT'LL SHUT HIM UP,
BE MY GUEST.
- ( both gasps ) - Mirajane:
WHOEVER YOU ARE, COME OUT!
- Azuma: RIDICULOUS.
FIRST CATS AND CHILDREN,
NOW TWO YOUNG LADIES?
- LISANNA, STAY BEHIND ME.
THIS GUY'S TROUBLE.
- COME ON, SIS,
I CAN HELP YOU!
- ( crying )
I'VE BEEN OUT HERE FOR HOURS!
WHY CAN'T I FIND ANYONE
IN THIS FOREST?! I'M SWEATY,
I'M HUNGRY AND I WANT
SOMEONE TO RUB MY BELLY!
( wails )
- MY LORD,
I'LL BE WITH YOU SOON.
- Hades: MAKAROV'S BRATS
DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THE SEVEN KIN
OF PURGATORY.
I'VE SPENT YEARS CRAFTING
THEM INTO SORCERERS
OF UNPARALLELED POWER.
EACH ONE OF THEM IS
A MASTER OF AN ART
THAT WAS BORN
FROM THE SOURCE OF ALL WIZARDRY:
FORBIDDEN LOST MAGIC!
FAIRY TAIL'S FINEST WILL
CRUMBLE LIKE DEAD LEAVES
UNDER THE KIN'S
OVERWHELMING MIGHT.
- ( cackles )
BRING IT ON, RUNT!
LET'S SEE IF I CAN
SCROUNGE A MEAL
OUT OF THOSE
PATHETIC FLAMES!
- I LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING
YOU CHOKE ON 'EM, FREAK!
MY FIST'LL BE
THE MAIN COURSE!
- AHHH.
I'M A GONER.
SOMEONE GIVE ME FOOD.
HEY, I THINK I HEAR
WATER NEARBY.
WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE FOR A NICE
TALL GLASS OF IT RIGHT NOW.
I THINK I'LL
JUST TAKE A NAP.
( whispers )
SOMEONE HELP ME.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: I'M THE ONLY
FIRE USER AROUND HERE!
- Happy: HE SAID HE
WAS A GOD SLAYER.
BUT WHEN YA THINK ABOUT IT,
WHAT EXACTLY IS A GOD ANYWAY?
- Natsu: THEY'RE THOSE
FUNNY-LOOKING VEGETABLES, RIGHT?
- NO, YOU'RE THINKIN' "GOURD."
- THEN IS IT WHAT LUCY
LIKES TO FLAUNT?
- NO, THAT'S HER "BOD."
- MAYBE IT'S LIKE THE STUFF
THAT FREAKAZOID DAPHNE
WAS TRYING TO--
- NO, THAT'S "FRAUD"!
- Natsu: JEEZ! WOULD YOU AT
LEAST LET ME
FINISH WHAT I'M SAYING?
- Happy: NATSU,
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER
I'D SAY YOU WERE MESSING
WITH ME ON PURPOSE.
- WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST CLUE?