There's no stoppin' us!
We've just started
to rock your world!
Fairy Tail will
be number one again!
[CROWD cheers]
[MATO] This changes everything.
I'll have to put a little
more thought into my plans.
Here's the battle
line-up, Boss.
I got a feeling you'll
find it very interesting.
[ALEXEI] Yes,
this one in particular.
It would appear that
there are some true
connoisseurs among
the event management.
It's about time we got started.
Raven Tail's true objective
is almost within reach.
[CHAPATI] We're halfway
through day three
of the Grand Magic Games,
so let's take a look at
the teams' current standings!
[CHAPATI] In first place
is the Raven Tail guild!
[cheering]
[ALEXEI] At long last,
the time has come.
Let's go. We've got work to do.
[ALL chuckle]
[CHAPATI] Holding on to
second place is Lamia Scale!
[CROWD cheers]
[CHAPATI] Dropping down to third
place is the Sabertooth guild!
[CROWD cheers]
[CHAPATI] In fourth place, it's
the ladies of Mermaid Heel!
[CROWD cheers]
Next we have the group
who jumped up two spots
to tie for fourth place, let's
hear it for Fairy Tail Team A!
[CROWD cheering]
Aw, yeah!
And we're gonna keep
climbing the ranks,
just you watch!
Aye, Sir!
[CHAPATI] In sixth place
is Fairy Tail Team B!
[CROWD cheers]
[GAJEEL] We can't let our
guild mates outdo us, guys.
[CHAPATI] And here are
the rest of the teams!
Wow, They don't
even announce your name
when you're in seventh place?
Oh, what an insulting parfum!
Good! If we've gotta
stick with "Quatro Puppy"
then I'm glad he ain't
announcin' our guild's name!
[HAPPY] Laxus versus Alexei!
[CHAPATI] Let's do away with the
pleasantries and shake up that
scoreboard with some
one-on-one battles!
[CROWD cheers]
Looking forward to it!
Should be exciting.
Indeed.
[CHAPATI] First up,
the kitten with major claws,
Mermaid Heel's Millianna.
[CHAPATI] Against Quattro
Puppy's towering giant, Semus!
Y'know we've got this one
in the bag, 'cause we're...
[ALL] Wild!
[CHAPATI] Let's get
this match started!
[SEMUS] First strike,
certain victory!
Wild Spin!
[CHAPATI] Look at that speed!
I never would've pegged him
as the fast and furious type!
[MILLIANNA] Hm. Guess I'll
just have to tie you up.
Bad Kitty Restraint Tube!
Ahhh!
It just bounced off!
[BETH, LISLIE, and ARAÑA]
Millianna, no!
That's it!
That's what ya get for
messin' with us, we're...
[YEAGER and NOVALI] Wild!
Ain't no way you
can beat us, kitty!
[MILLIANNA grunts]
I'm just gettin' started!
[SEMUS] Wild!
Eat this! Kitten Blast!
[SEMUS] All your
attack did was make me
spin even faster! Take this!
[MILLIANNA screams]
Alright, give her
a good thrashin'!
We're gonna win this
round because we're...
[ALL] Wild!
Oh, wow! Do you think
Millianna can beat him?
She's not givin' up but
she's taken major damage.
I'm worried.
She's going to be fine.
It won't be that easy to defeat
a warrior like Millianna.
Come on! Fight!
Stay strong, 'kay?
There is someone out there
who Millianna needs to defeat.
And until she does that,
she will not lose.
[MILLIANNA] I'd be
a bad kitty if I lost
to a weakling like you.
And It would mean I joined
Mermaid Heel for nothing!
It's time to finish you off!
[SEMUS] Wild Spin,
Double Speed!
[CHAPATI] He kicks
it into high gear,
but will it be enough
to finish the match?
I'll put ya in a Bad
Kitty Restraint Tube!
[SEMUS] I'll rip
that thing to shreds!
Well, Good luck 'cause
I'm not lettin' go!
Ah!
[SEMUS] I'm down but still wild.
[MILLIANNA] Meow.
Man, there ain't nothin'
wild about losin'.
[ALL] Aw...
I'm feelin' pretty pumped up!
[CHAPATI] Millianna's treating
the arena like her own
personal cat box, and she's
got something big to bury!
[cheering]
[MILLIANNA] Meow!
[YAJIMA] That was
one of the best battles
I've seen in a while!
[LAHAR] There are so many
varieties of magic that
have been used in the games
so far. It's quite fascinating.
She's come a long way.
I'm proud of her.
Her score on the Magic
Power Finder was enough
to convince me
that she's strong,
but she's downright
scary with those tubes.
Yeah, no kidding.
Real scary.
Gotta admit, even I had
a hard time against her
back in the day.
I have never
stopped hating Jellal.
Okay, moving on to the second
match of the battle segment.
[CHAPATI] Let's hear it
for the "minstrel who sings
to the red moon,"
Sabertooth's Rufus Lore!
[FEMALE CROWD cheers]
[CHAPATI] He'll be facing
off against Blue Pegasus'
"Holy Night," Eve Tilm!
[CROWD cheers]
Go, Eve! May you have
the parfum of victory!
You can beat this clown!
You've got
this man! Yeah!
[CHAPATI] Rufus spanked
the little guy on day one.
But will he get
his comeuppance today?
Snow Magic, Blow White Fury!
[RUFUS] What you struck
was merely a memory of me.
Hm?
[EVE] I got a taste
of your techniques
during the Hidden game.
And I've got 'em
all memorized now!
Oh really,
is that so? Well...
Man.
[EVE] Master Ichiya? What
the heck are you doin' here?
Seems you've been fooled
by your own memory.
[EVE] Ahhh!
[ICHIYA] Man.
Don't tell me this is
somewhere deep in his memory!
Yeah, no kidding. You've got
some explaining to do, sir!
Please believe me when I
say that I have absolutely
no memory of this
scandalous perfum, man!
[RUFUS] Night of Shooting Stars!
Oh! Eve has taken
a direct hit from Rufus!
[CHAPATI] Well, I'll be!
Turns out it was just
a copy made of snow!
Now that is an
impressive perfum!
All right! Score!
Show him how we do it!
If I'm not mistaken, Eve
used to work for the Council,
didn't he?
[LAHAR] That's right.
It was many years ago,
but he started off as a Custody
Enforcement Rune Knight,
much like myself.
[LAHAR] Even back
then it was obvious
he possessed incredible talent.
But it appears his
magic skills have grown
since joining the
Blue Pegasus guild.
[EVE] White Blizzard!
You know that's pointless.
Yeah right,
that's what you think!
My White Blizzard
may not look like much
but it's gonna help me win
by finding the real you!
Right there!
Go get 'im White Fang!
[RUFUS] I've already
memorized that spell.
I'll counter it
with Memory Make.
That's it!
Maker magic. But I've
never heard of it before.
[ULTEAR] He uses magic that
can give form to memories?
Impossible.
Long-forgotten magic.
It's an ancient spell.
I'm not quite sure what
you mean, First Master,
are you trying to say there's
more to it than meets the eye?
[CHAPATI] Great googly-moogly!
What's happening down there?
[YAJIMA] It looks like this
fight is starting to warm up.
[LAHAR] I'm sensing an
incredible surge in magic power.
♪
Karma of the Scorching Earth!
Ahhh!
[bell dinging]
[CHAPATI]
And that's the match, folks!
[cheering and screaming]
[CHAPATI] And it looks like
this "Holy Night" is over.
Eve is gonna feel
that in the morning.
[CHAPATI] That nets another
win for Sabertooth's Rufus!
The man is on fire!
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH] Ha-ha!
[GRAY]
So he uses Maker magic, too.
I guess that means it's
up to me to defeat him.
Can't believe that little
punk lost the match. Damn.
But it's okay, 'cause
he put up a good fight.
Hey Meister. Our team's
rank has fallen significantly.
What'll we do?
Rest easy, my lads,
like the languid parfum
of a fragrant flower.
We have a secret
weapon that is certain
to lead us to victory!
Yes, we have a secret weapon.
It's so important that I had
to mention it to you twice.
[REN and HIBIKI]
Very informative, Sir.
I'm happy for the help
but I really wish I knew
who was inside the bunny suit.
It's kinda weird that
he's refusing to tell us.
Hold up. Do you think it's
someone who's not in our guild?
Sometimes you gotta bend the
rules to get what you want.
[MATO] And now, it's time for
the third match of the day!
[CHAPATI] Bringing the lightning
is Fairy Tail B's Laxus Dreyar.
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] Going up
against the mysterious man
in the metal mask,
Raven Tail's Alexei.
Kick his butt!
Of course it's someone
from Ivan's guild.
Good luck!
You can do it, Laxus!
I got no doubt that
we're gonna win this one.
It is Laxus, after all.
Yes, but still, I've got a
really bad feeling about this.
♪
Last time we saw these
two guilds go head to head,
the outcome was pretty
brutal for Fairy Tail.
Mhmmm.
'Scuse me, Lahar.
Did you happen to bring any
of your men here with you?
Yes, sir. A few.
As per regulations.
I want you to keep a close
eye on Raven Tail, okay?
If you see anything
suspicious, lemme know
and I'll have them
stop the match.
Right.
Warren.
I'm on it sir!
[WARREN] This is HQ!
Do you read me, Bisca?
[BISCA] Yeah but what's
with the lame "HQ" stuff?
No activity from
Master Ivan yet. Over.
Roger that!
Now let's hear from team
Thunder Legion and
Lisanna. You see Anything?
[LISANNA] Team Thunder
Legion and Lisanna reporting.
We haven't spotted any unusual
activity from Raven Tail.
They might've been able
to trick us on day one;
not this time!
Let it be known that if
you dare to dishonor Laxus,
the Thunder Legion will pounce.
You scoundrels will be lucky
if you make it out alive.
Hey Master, Ever
has been whining about
wanting to be by Elfman's side.
So would ya give
her permission? Over!
I have not, you liar!
Ivan, my children and
I won't put up with
any more of
your trickery.
[chuckles]
What's so funny,
First Master? Tell me.
Oh, nothing!
Sorry, I'm just happy.
The guild is ready to
do whatever it takes
to keep their friends safe.
It's nice. Even though
they're focused on their task,
they still manage
to have a little fun.
Eh!
[giggles]
It's wonderful!
[MAVIS] This is precisely
the guild I set out to create!
Please, promise me that
it'll stay like this.
[MAVIS] Don't forget
this is how the guild
was meant to be, Third Master.
Oh, sorry. You're the
Sixth Master now, aren't you?
[MAKAROV] Hm. Thank you!
That's music to my ears!
But one thing, I'm
the Seventh Master.
[MACAO] No, you're the sixth!
[WAKABA] Get it
together, Gramps!
[CHAPATI]
Competitors, step forward!
[CHAPATI] Let the battle begin!
[cheering]
[LAXUS] A mysterious member
of my old man's guild.
Nice mask. Wanna tell
me who you really are?
[LAXUS] Ah!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[LAXUS] Who is this guy?
[LAXUS groans]
Aaahhh!
Oh, no!
You gotta be kiddin' me!
I can't believe
he's losing.
He makes beating
Laxus look easy!
Yeah. That Alexei
guy is scary!
That masked freak!
Who in the hell is he?
Is this for real? He's losing?
Incredible! Alexei strikes with
a fierce uppercut to the jaw!
He's left Laxus
completely powerless!
[BOTH] Hm...
[LAXUS] Care to explain
what's goin' on here?
[ALEXEI] A type
of illusory magic.
It's the only way we could
have a private conversation.
Those around us
cannot see or hear us,
even though we're standing
right in front of them.
They're watching an illusion
of the two of us fighting.
[ALEXEI] Incredibly
convincing, isn't it?
Not a single person has noticed.
They're too busy
watching you struggle
to stand your ground
in a losing fight.
[MAKAROV] I never thought Laxus
would be at such a disadvantage!
Well, Bisca?
There's been no
movement from Ivan!
[WARREN] Lisanna,
you guys see anything?
Nothing new to report.
They're just standing there!
Come on! Fight Back!
I know that you've still
got some fight left in you!
Yeah, listen to 'im!
Don't give up! You can
still take him, Laxus!
[ALEXEI] It must be nice
to know your guild mates
hold you in such high regard.
I'm sure they're
absolutely heartbroken.
Watching you fall to
your enemy like this.
Throw down some lightning!
[ALL gasp]
I don't get it.
This plan of yours
doesn't make any sense at all.
[ALEXEI] No?
What's the point in
beating me with an illusion?
I mean, can you
call that a win?
[ALEXEI] Obviously,
victory in this match
is not our ultimate goal.
The purpose of the illusion is
to distract those around us.
[LAXUS] Huh?
[ALEXEI] And if I
control the illusion,
I control the outcome
of the match as well.
Control it? How so?
[NATSU, WENDY, GRAY,
and LUCY] Laxus!
Show him what you can do!
Stay strong!
[LAXUS struggling]
[grunts]
Whoa! It looks
as though Laxus
is back in the game,
ladies and gentlemen!
[grunting]
--[ALL cheering]
--[MAKAROV] Aw, yeah!
That's the spirit, Laxus m'boy!
Yes! There ya go!
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
Well, he's
finally back in action.
Seems that way.
[LAXUS yells]
--[WARREN] Hm-hrmmm!
--[MAKAROV] Yeah!
That oughta do it!
After all that, we had
no reason to worry. Right?
Yep!
[WARREN] Thanks for
the help, Bisca!
Sure thing.
[WARREN] Lisanna, you and
the Thunder Legion rocked too!
Glad they
didn't try anything.
To think that I was
honestly worried about him
losing for a second
there! Silly me!
[LAXUS] Ahhhh--uh!
--[ALL gasp]
--[MAKAROV] What the--?
No, Laxus!
[CHAPATI] And just like that,
the tables have turned again!
Laxus better step it up
or he'll be dead meat!
Get up, man!
What in the hell
is goin' on here?
So that's your idea of
controlling the match.
Y'think I care?
[ALEXEI] The point is,
I can arrange for you to win
this match depending on
how our negotiations fare.
[LAXUS] Ain't no way
I'm fallin' for that.
I don't really give a crap
about your stupid illusion.
But I can't wait to get
my hands on the real you
so I can defeat ya here and now!
[FLARE] That's not
going to happen.
[chuckles]
Reality can be
pretty harsh sometimes.
[ALEXEI]
Your power is impressive,
but not even the
strongest of wizards
could defeat all of
Raven Tail at once.
[BLACKSNAKE chuckles]
[ALEXEI] There's one
more thing to consider.
[IVAN] I'm sure you're aware
of just how powerful I am.
Aren't you, my boy?
Y'know, I had a feeling
you were behind that mask.
My deadbeat dad.
[IVAN] Makarov would rather
die than reveal the secret.
[grunting]
On the other hand,
you're a different story.
[IVAN] Surely I can
depend on my son.
Now, tell me where to
find the Lumen Histoire.
Sorry, never heard of it.
Don't try to play dumb with me.
[LAXUS] I'm not.
If Makarov was to tell anyone
it would be his
beloved grandson.
Guess not 'cause I don't know
what you're talkin' about.
He must have told you
something about it!
Nope, but even if
the old, geezer had,
it's not like I
would ever tell you.
[IVAN] Come now. I'm offering
you the opportunity
to emerge victorious
from what is otherwise
an utterly hopeless situation.
[IVAN] If you dare
to refuse my terms...
your illusory form
won't be the only one
getting a thrashing.
You think you can scare me?
Better think again, old man.
[LAXUS] It's no wonder the
old geezer gave up on you.
Come at me. All of you.
If you're an enemy of
Fairy Tail's master,
then that makes
you my enemy, too.
[IVAN] I think it's
about time for your father
to teach you an
important lesson.
The guild standing before you
was created for one reason.
To take down Fairy
Tail once and for all.
[FLARE and NALPUDDING chuckle]
[OBRA and BLACKSNAKE chuckle]
[RAVEN TAIL chucikles]
[NATSU] I wish I knew what
was goin' on with Laxus.
[HAPPY] What if those
Raven Tail jerks are up to
their old tricks again?
[NATSU] I doubt that.
Everybody's watching 'em.
[HAPPY] Maybe he's
just havin' a bad day
and it's throwin' him off.
[NATSU] Like he ate
too much last night
and now he's feelin' sick?
[HAPPY] Or he drank too much!
[NATSU] Yeah! Wait, I bet
it's a personal problem!
He's prob'ly lonely 'cause he
doesn't have that many friends.
[HAPPY and NATSU] Next time:
"Wendy versus Shelia!"
[HAPPY] Nah, I know
what's buggin' him.
[NATSU] Oh, yeah? What?
[HAPPY] The poor guy's
gotta be worn out...
from dealin'
with your stupidity!
[laughs]