[HAPPY]
Look at all of the writing.
And that big floating
sphere in the center.
Doesn't it look like a globe?
[CARLA] This must be some
kind of command center.
[FRANMALTH]
How could they make it this far?
Those worthless guards couldn't
be more pathetic if they tried.
[LUCY]
Hey. Do you see that?
[WENDY gasps]
I had hoped Erza was wrong,
but it looks like the
Face has been unsealed.
How do we stop it?
Could we use this magic circle?
Maybe it could seal
it all over again.
Perhaps. But there's no
way for us to operate it.
We're locked out.
Hold on.
If I'm reading this right,
the Face can only be activated
by its on-site controls.
We might be in luck here.
It's already started?
[FRANMALTH chuckles]
[FRANMALTH] You sure work
fast, Ezel. Well done.
Oh no!
[LUCY gasps]
I don't wanna
jump to conclusions,
but this looks like a countdown.
[gasps]
[screaming]
Theres only 41 more minutes.
Then all magic on the continent
will be purged from existence!
You brat! I'll kill you!
Well, if the small fries
aren't goin' to cut it,
I have no choice but to show
you my most powerful soul!
You asked for this!
[FRANMALTH groaning]
[NARRATOR] Face, a pulse
bomb with the power
to destroy all magic on the
continent, is counting down.
Most of Fairy Tail
fights in the Cube:
Home of the demons of Zeref
who set Face to work
against mankind.
But In a last ditch effort
to prevent the detonation,
Wendy and Carla fly
out on their own.
Time is a precious resource,
and Fairy Tail's is running out.
Can Wendy's team
succeed in its mission?
Or will our heroes soon dwell
in a world without magic?
[WENDY]
We have to hurry, Carla!
[CARLA]
I realize that.
We can't afford to mess this up.
The stakes are bigger than us.
The whole continent's at risk.
No matter what happens,
we have to find a way.
[CARLA] I agree, but I have
no idea what we should try.
Neither do I.
We'll have to improvise.
I know that's what
Natsu would do.
Failure's not an option.
You've gotta fly even faster,
Carla! As fast as you can!
Whoa, that smoke.
[LUCY gasps]
Crazy.
This shouldn't be possible.
How does he...?
How does he have that soul?
[LUCY]
It's Master Hades.
Bullcrap. It's totally off!
[laughing]
You don't even have
the body right!
[LUCY]
I don't like it.
The nuances of my appearance
aren't important.
Don't you get it? I've become
the dark wizard Hades!
[NATSU] I can see that's
what your goin' for.
Can you?
Because if you could then you'd
be cowering in fear right now.
Obviously you have no idea
what a scary man he was.
Yeah, no. I remember
him pretty well.
[LUCY] He caused us a lotta
trouble back in the day.
[HAPPY]
Judgin' from that costume,
we knew him way better than you.
That's enough! Shut
your wretched traps
and I will tell you all you
never knew about him!
You may have heard of the
dark guild, Grimoire Heart.
Well this man, a man after
my own heart, led the thing!
He was the darkest genius the
world had seen since Zeref.
Now feel free to
grovel at my feet!
[LUCY]
We said we know who he was.
[HAPPY] You need to work
on your listening skills.
Seven years ago, as I was
searching for Lord Zeref,
I stumbled upon this
fabulous hunk of carrion.
This man was human in name
alone, because everything
from his taste in books to his
better eye radiated with power.
Demonic power!
[HAPPY] So you never heard about
how Hades got beat, didja?
Can't say I have,
but I don't see why that
would matter to me.
[chuckles] Oh, it matters.
'Cause it was me who kicked
his wrinkled butt!
Wha--?
I already won this
fight seven years ago.
It's how my flames
got their spark.
Yeah, man, Natsu already gave
that Hades guy the business.
But did you fight him alone?
[yelling]
[NATSU yells]
[LUCY]
Natsu!
The body might not
look like much,
but once it's revved
up, it doesn't quit!
[NATSU growls]
Such power can
only come from those
who've seen the
Abyss of Sorcery!
Got ya!
There we go. Connection!
Soon I'll be putting
your soul in the bank!
[NATSU]
Naw, I don't think so!
Lightning Flame Dragon mode!
Lightning Flame Dragon Roar!
It's like getting cooked
in a stormcloud!
[yelping]
[screaming]
Ooh. I've never had
such a spicy soul.
[NATSU]
Huh?
Let me absorb it!
[gasps]
Say what now?
So he can nom on the
souls of Natsu's spells?
I didn't even know that
spells could have souls.
[laughing]
I gotta say, that was
yummy little snack.
Sure didn't see that one comin'.
[FRANMALTH] I can feel
the scope of your strength
from the taste you gave me.
You're likely the wizard
who beat Jackal,
but that doesn't speak for
your odds with the rest of us.
'Cause we're all demons
of the Books of Zeref.
Each of us a unique and living
weapon from a far better time.
Expertly crafted by
the cruelest of hands.
You'd do yourself a service
by keeping sight of the fact
that each of us has the
strength of a full army.
And a lust for human pain.
[SEILAH] You've no chance
against my Macro curse.
With it, I can force
any human being
to do exactly as I bid them.
So that's how you were able to
get Elfman to destroy our guild.
Well then.
Listen, demon.
You hurt my siblings. That means
you'll have to answer to me.
And I'm not as nice as I seem.
Careful, sis! She's
trying to provoke you.
A reckless charge is
exactly what she wants!
Humans are quite easily
swayed by their emotions.
This makes you simple
to manipulate.
On such foolish beings,
my powers are wasted.
[gasps]
Those "foolish emotions"
are also a source of
humanity's strength.
[MIRAJANE yells]
Satan Soul Mirajane.
Your human rage is
nothing to the pen of Zeref.
Mirajane, behind you!
This is Mirajane's
strongest form,
and she still isn't winning.
I will not lose.
[KYOKA yells]
Such power.
I'll ask you once again.
What is your guild
trying to accomplish?
You say you wish to return to
Zeref, but what does that mean?
We live to serve the great
being who created us.
As he has made his
wishes quite clear,
there is but one
path set before us.
The destruction of your world.
Don't expect all to go
according to your plan.
My comrades'll be fighting
to stop Face as we speak!
[KYOKA] You speak of our plans,
but yours are just as fragile.
[ERZA]
What?
[chuckling]
[ERZA] That smile, as if
she's predicted all of this.
Still, plans are the last
thing you should worry about.
Just hang in there.
We're getting close!
[CARLA] Don't worry.
I'll get us there, somehow.
[GRAY] Listen, man. I'm in
a bit of a rush, all right?
So either tell me why you're
bringin' up this "Silver" guy,
or shut up and come at me!
[KEYES chuckles]
This freak has the
same defense as Juvia.
What the heck are you doin'?
If you're gonna
fight, then fight!
[KEYES]
Tartaros does have a member
who might match your
strength, but I am not he.
The hell, man? Are you tryin'
to beat me, or take me home?
Because either way,
I'm not that easy!
[KEYES]
Think what you will.
It matters not.
[GRAY]
I can't land a single hit.
[KEYES]
With power like yours,
you could cause
quite the disruption.
I think I'll hold
you here instead.
So that means you're just
tryin' to keep me busy.
[ELFMAN yelling]
[SOLDIER A]
Six men, one punch?
[SOLDIER B]
I counted seven.
That was barely even a warm up!
I've got a lot more
manly atonement ahead!
[SOLDIER C yelling]
[ELFMAN yells]
Mirajane! Lisanna!
Where are you?
Your sisters are strong, Elfman,
if anyone can hold out
in here, it's them.
So instead of worrying,
have faith and focus!
They'd do the same for you.
Yeah, you're right.
Those two are manly.
They're gonna be fine,
the both of 'em. I know it.
I think that's the Poison
Jelly Valley cavern.
Take us inside.
[WENDY]
Wow. How deep is it?
[CARLA] It'll be hard
to locate Face in this.
[CARLA]
I apologize, Wendy.
It seems that I used
up too much magic.
[WENDY]
Don't worry. You were awesome.
Hey, look. A tunnel.
Let's check it out.
I'm no gambler, but
against demonic curses,
human magic has worse odds
than a three-legged
goat in a lion's den.
Oh, and countdown update.
If you're going to win
against those odds,
you'd better do it in
the next ten minutes,
or else you'll have
no magic to fight with.
I'll have to ask
you how it feels.
Once the magic's been torn away
from you, tell me what's left!
Something tells me you
don't really give a crap
about our feelings, do ya?
Wish we knew exactly
how much time was left.
You have a remaining
9 minutes and 43 seconds.
[LUCY] Everyone who can stand
is fighting right now.
If we lose our magic all
at once, we'd be doomed.
[JUVIA]
What is that?
[ELFMAN]
Whatever it is,
let's deal with it fast so
we can find my sisters!
[roaring]
[WAKABA] Damn it! Looks like
we'll be on our own for a while.
[MACAO]
It doesn't matter.
Where d'ya think we'll find
the guy with the Bane Particles?
How would I know?
Let's just keep fightin'
and hope we run into him.
If we can somehow pull this off,
I'm gettin' drunk tonight.
[WAKABA]
I'm up for that!
[LUCY] Nine minutes.
That's all we have left.
[LUCY] If Face detonates,
there'll be nothing we can do.
It's all up to Wendy.
Just Wendy, that's it.
[HAPPY]
Hey, she's gonna be fine.
She's not alone.
Carla's with her,
and Carla's one smart cookie!
Whatever they're up against,
I'm sure she'll figure it out.
[WENDY]
It's getting even darker.
There was a distant
light near the entrance,
but now I can barely
see where I'm walking.
[CARLA groans]
Hey, I'm sorry
I pushed you so hard.
I'll be fine. Just need a nap.
But first let's find this Face
device and neutralize it.
Well, the problem is we don't
know the first thing about it.
I couldn't even tell you
what it looks like.
What do you think Natsu
would do if he was here?
[CARLA] I suspect that
he would go buck-wild
and destroy the entire cave.
But I'm not nearly as
strong as Natsu, so I can't.
I'm glad for that.
Natsu would've brought the
whole thing crashing down on us.
Why don't you just try
to feel for magic power?
Yeah, good point.
I'll give that a shot.
[WENDY sniffs]
[rustling]
[WENDY]
Hm?
[WENDY yelps]
[WENDY screaming]
[WENDY]
Do you know where we came from?
'Cause I'm definitely lost now.
Be calm.
Settle down, and take
a nice, deep breath.
If you say so.
[WENDY inhales]
[WENDY exhales]
[WENDY]
Wow, this air's amazing.
[CARLA] It's certainly moist and
cool. Did it clear your head?
Well yeah, but I feel like there
might be more to it than that.
Now that you mention
it, I think I'm--
I think I'm on the verge
of realizing something.
Yeah?
Yes, but I'm too exhausted
to focus properly.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
I feel like it might
be important, but--
[EZEL] What kind of
pathetic morsels are these?
Kyoka's playing me for a fool.
You two won't even come
close to filling me up.
[WENDY gasps]
[EZEL] But I guess
you'll do for a snack!
It's a demon. He must be the
one they sent to activate Face!
[EZEL]
That's right!
I was told that Fairy Tail would
send someone to try and stop us.
I only took this job 'cause
Kyoka said I could eat 'em!
I was hoping to have a feast!
Well, looks like
the jokes on me!
What do we do now?
We can't fight, we only
have a few minutes left!
Come back here. I'm starving!
[CARLA]
Even if we did have time,
you're not nearly strong
enough to take him on alone!
[EZEL roars]
He's gonna catch us!
I don't have a choice!
[CARLA]
Wendy, don't!
Enhancing all elemental
resistances! Deus Corona!
Enhancing all physical
abilities! Deus Eques!
Swift Winds, Stalwart Might,
and Steel Resolve of
the heavens combine!
Enchantment!
You know this won't save you.
Sky Dragon Roar!
[gasps]
That wasn't bad, pipsqueak!
No. But it's about to be my
turn. And this will end it all!
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon Talon!
[chuckles]
It did nothing.
Swords of Tenka Goken!
Don't just stand
there, take cover!
Onimaru!
[laughing]
Juzumaru!
Wendy, look out!
[gasps]
[WENDY] I used every defense I
have, but he's still too strong.
[WENDY screaming]
[WENDY yelps]
[EZEL]
Behold.
[WENDY gasps]
[EZEL]
You will die beside Face.
No, I... can't.
[EZEL]
It detonates in five minutes.
Hopefully that'll dissipate
the stench of ether-nano.
It's brutal at this range.
Kills my appetite.
Wait, ether-nano?
[gasps]
[EZEL] With the treatment
this stuff's getting,
it'll become the end
of all other ether-nano,
and all magic too.
Just five minutes till
our curses reign supreme!
Face's ether-nano.
If we can smell it,
that must mean it's seeping
into the air somehow.
[groaning]
Lucky for you,
that five minute countdown'll
take longer than your death.
[screaming]
Unhand Wendy, you monster!
Take this! And this too!
I'm sorry, Carla.
I'll scratch your
eyes out. Let her go!
Carla... you have to run.
Let her go! Take me instead!
[CARLA]
Come on then!
Don't hurt her!
Please, put her down!
That's a weird lookin' cat.
Still, it looks edible.
Stop! Don't do this,
I'm begging you!
No!
Wendy... the air.
[gasps]
[WENDY] This wonderful air.
That breath I took.
Face is permeated with
high-density ether-nano.
There's so much of the stuff
that the air around
Face is swathed in it.
If I could ingest it
like Natsu did.
If I could just...
breathe it in,
it might make me strong
enough to save Carla.
[WENDY yelling]
[EZEL grunts]
Whoa! What was that?
[CARLA] Wendy used to
seem so weak and timid.
I thought I'd always
have to protect her.
I was wrong. She got
stronger every day.
And now she has
the Dragon Force.
[LUCY]
Right when we needed her most,
Wendy finally obtained
the Dragon Force.
Now, as Face continues
its countdown to the end,
her fight with the
demon Ezel begins anew.
As that fight draws
to a close, however,
Wendy and Carla are
confronted by a new horror.
This one comes in
the form of a choice.
And perhaps a sacrifice too.
Next Time: "Tartaros Chapter
Friends Forever."
The smallest amongst us,
have the courage of giants.