[NARRATOR] It's time
once again for Fiore's
annual spectacle of sorcery,
the Grand Magic Games.
To make up for the
seven years of training
the team lost on Tenrow Island,
Natsu and the others began an
intensive three-month regimen.
And now...
♪
[NARRATOR] Their training
completed, the weary members
of Fairy Tail assemble
at the guildhall once again.
[moaning and groaning]
Home, sweet home.
[MACAO] Are you guys just
gonna lay around all day?
Get up!
Huh?
Yeah, stand up!
C'mon and get on your feet
like a bunch of real men!
[HAPPY] Crocus,
the Flower-Blooming Capital!
[NATSU] Wow Elfman,
you really packed
on some muscle there, big guy!
[LISANNA] The three of
us all trained super hard up
in the mountains
for the past few months.
[ELFMAN] I've got the muscles
every real man dreams of!
Well I've hit my own
milestone over the
past three months, and now I can
finally eat fermented soybeans!
[WARREN] And I'm proud
to announce that I've
overcome my once-crippling
fear of heights.
I don't think those things
will be very helpful to us.
My honey-gun
and I have got our
sharpshooting skills
to an all-time high.
[ALZACK] Bam!
And I was able to
finish reading an entire
a 30-volume horror novel series!
[MACAO] All you
got done was reading?
[WAKABA] You could've at least
read some books on dieting.
My Sand Storm is more powerful
than it's ever been before.
I bet I could even beat
Natsu if we fought again!
Oh yeah?
[MAKAROV] Good work, everyone!
[NATSU] Oh!
Hey Gramps!
[MAKAROV] It appears that
you've all trained very hard
to prepare for the
Grand Magic Games.
[LUCY THINKS] Um. I wouldn't
go that far, exactly.
[MAKAROV] Right now, I'd like
everybody to join me inside.
Listen up kids!
It's time to announce
the five who'll be
representing Fairy Tail
in the Grand Magic Games.
[MAKAROV] Natsu!
Oh yeah1
[MAKAROV] Gray!
I'm honored.
[MAKAROV] Erza!
I won't let you down.
Of course...
Those three were kind
of a shoo-in for the team.
Who will get the
last two spots?
We're gonna need a real
man to represent our guild.
[JUVIA THINKS] I don't want Gray
to go into battle without me.
[MAKAROV]
And the remaining two will be.
[MAKAROV] Lucy and Wendy!
[WENDY AND LUCY] Huh?
[ELFMAN] How humiliating.
Seriously?
Those two?
[JUVIA THINKS] My darling will
be locked in mortal
combat without me at his side?
I can't bear to think about it!
But I'm not a fighter, master!
Can't you pick Laxus or
Gajeel for the team instead?
I don't really have
that option because
neither of them
has come back yet.
We weren't chosen
for our individual strength.
but our combined
strength as a team.
So let's make him
proud and give it our all.
Right, good point.
Yeah!
I'll do my very best!
I think we'd have much
more of a fighting
chance with Laxus
and Gajeel on the team.
But my hands are tied here.
[NATSU AND GRAY] We can hear
what you're sayin', ya know?
Alright team!
The Grand Magic Games present
a perfect opportunity for
us to reclaim the prominence
that we once held!
Today Sabertooth is regarded
as Fiore's number one guild.
Let us take that title!
Fairy Tail will be
the top guild again!
[ALL] Yeah!
Now I've got
a fire in my belly!
[LUCY] And now.
This majestic city is Crocus.
The "Flower-Blooming Capital"
of the Fiore kingdom!
[LUCY] Once a year,
a huge festival of wizardry,
the Grand Magic Games,
are held in its borders.
The streets are filled with
excitement and the hustle
and bustle of hopeful wizards
and curious spectators alike.
[LUCY] At the heart
of it all stands the king
of Fiore's castle, the
luminaria palace, Mercurius.
[LUCY] Sitting atop a mountain
to the west of the city,
is Domus Flau,
the coliseum where the
Grand Magic Games are held.
[LUCY] And huddled somewhere
among all this craziness, is us.
I can't believe I
still feel so horrible.
I really hope that whole
Second Origin-unleashing
spell wasn't just
some kind of sick joke
to make us lose the contest.
I do sorta feel like
I have more magic power.
Everything else in my body
feels like I got hit by a train.
[ERZA] Chin up!
There's no time for whining.
[LUCY] Why aren't you feeling
like death on a cracker?
[GRAY] My guess is she's
always had her Second Origin.
[LUCY] That makes perfect sense.
I don't think I've
ever been in such
a humongous city
before in my life!
Aye!
[WENDY] Yeah, me either.
[CARLA] It certainly puts
Edolas' castle city to shame.
[MAKAROV]
I see you kids finally made it.
[ERZA] Master!
We've just now finished
with the registration process.
So let's show everyone
why Fairy Tail
is the number
one guild in Fiore!
Hey, it looks like the
Fairy Tail guild is here!
[MALE CITIZEN 155B]
Those clowns?
Well, somebody's gotta
come in last place, right?
Hey... are those
jerks laughing at us?
Easy.
Come on, you guys finish
in last place every single year.
Everybody knows Sabertooth
is takin' the top spot.
If anyone wants to laugh,
they can do it all they want.
Sounds like
a good time to me!
[JET AND DROY] Hey you don't
have to laugh at us, cat!
Don't forget, we're doing
this for the thirty mill--
I mean, we're doing
this for the honor of
being Fiore's top
ranked guild, of course.
[MAKAROV] Our founding
master rose from her eternal
slumber to save our lives,
so let's make her proud!
[MAKAROV] Now then, we know that
the games will begin tomorrow.
[MAKAROV] But unfortunately,
we don't know what they'll be.
What?
I thought you guys
did this every year.
[ALZACK] Yeah, but the
games change every year.
[ASCA] Pick me up, daddy!
The year my sugar-pistol
and I didn't participate,
they had a big ol'
target shooting game.
And the year that I decided to
sit out, there was a foot-race.
They take the teams
scores over a bunch
of different contests
to determine the winner.
They like to mix it up.
I looked through records
from the previous games.
And there's no real
consistency to them.
Well, then we'll just
have to play it by ear!
But I hope there's
some kinda fight!
Every year we sense unusual
magic power during the games.
[ERZA THINKS]
Mysterious magic power,
and the games are a
mystery as well?
[MAKAROV] Erza...
I'd like you to read through the
official rulebook by tomorrow.
I'm to read all this?
[LEVY] Aw, don't worry!
I have my Wind-Reader
Glasses with me!
Levy to the rescue!
[LEVY] Okay, to sum it all up...
I would say there
are three major rules.
The first one is the
master of each guild
isn't allowed
to participate.
[MAKAROV]
Sounds sensible enough.
[LEVY] A guild can't have
anybody that doesn't bear their
respective emblem
take part on its behalf.
[GRAY] Kinda took
that one as a given.
[LEVY] And every game will
remain a mystery until the very
moment it is announced,
and only then will the
game's rules be
explained in detail.
Well, that's certainly
not very helpful.
[LEVY] This one
could be important, too.
All participants
must return to their
designated inn by
twelve o' clock.
There's a curfew?
[LUCY] What time again?
[CARLA] I suppose they
mean midnight tonight.
Or what, we all
turn into pumpkins?
That reminds me
of the story about the
princess and the glass slipper.
[JUVIA THINKS] So my darling
only talks about tales of
romance and lost
love when I'm not around?
Oh, my icy Prince!
[NATSU] Cool, we've got
tons of time until midnight!
And since this is everyone's
first time in the capital.
Let's go check it out!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
[LUCY] Wait for me!
[ERZA] Hold on!
Do you know where we're staying?
[LUCY] The Honey
Bone Inn, right?
[ERZA] Just be sure to
be back by twelve o' clock!
You hear me?
[HAPPY] Aye!
[ERZA THINKS] I wonder what's
so important about that time.
[NARRATOR] Tonight,
the members representing the
Fairy Tail guild
will be staying here.
The Honey Bone Inn.
[ERZA] For some reason six
beds have been prepared.
Does this mean we'll all
be sharing the same room?
Nothing appears to
be out of the ordinary here.
[JUVIA] Gray, my darling!
[GRAY]
Hey, didn't expect to see you.
You come all this
way by yourself?
I'm not the only one, silly.
The entire guild came
here to cheer you on!
[GRAY] I guess nobody's
busy takin' on any jobs, huh?
[JUVIA] What do you
think about you and I
going to get a bite
to eat somewhere?
[GRAY] Yeah, sure.
I am getting pretty hungry.
Lucky for you,
I know of a perfect
restaurant not far from here.
Lyon!
[LYON] It's quite
romantic, actually.
Complete with an
aquarium filled with
beautiful creatures
from the sea.
[JUVIA] Oh yeah?
Well.
I, uh.
Hey man, you
can't just go runnin'
away with one of
our guild members!
[LYON] Rumor has it that you're
entering the Grand Magic Games.
Right?
Yeah?
[LYON] It's no use.
For Lamia Scale will surely
emerge as the victor.
[GRAY] I thought you guys
always came in second place.
And your guild always
comes in last place.
But this year will be different
for us because Jura and I
will be participating in the
games for the very first time.
That means we'll be
stronger than ever before.
Well, we happen
to have our own
ace-in-the hole
known as Erza Scarlet.
So don't count us
out of the race just yet.
Let's make a friendly wager.
If Lamia Scale wins the
Grand Magic Games this year,
then the beautiful Juvia
will become part of our guild!
[GRAY] Are you serious?
And, what if we win?
If your guild wins,
we'll give her back.
She's already a member
of our guild, you bonehead!
This is a gentleman's
agreement.
So don't forget it, Gray.
This has got to be
the absolute stupidest
bet that I've ever heard of!
The words of a man
afraid to lose.
Oh, I ain't afraid.
My darling Gray, please
don't torture us any longer!
Do you want to be with Lyon
or the woman who loves you?
You have to make
up your mind already!
[GRAY] You really don't have a
clue what's going on, do you?
[JELLAL] You always
know what to say, don't you?
[ERZA] That's not true at all.
I just stumble through
life one day at a time.
That's all
[ICHIYA] Erza.
Your fragrant parfum is
as intoxicating as I remember.
Sniff, sniff!
Sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff!
[ERZA]
You need to respect my privacy!
Got it?
[ICHIYA] Man!
[EVE] You're so beautiful
when you're angry.
[REN] We didn't come here
to make you feel better,
so don't get the wrong idea.
[HIBIKI]
Would you like to freshen up?
[ERZA] Why don't you follow
your little troll of a master?
[ALL] Trimens forever!
[kids cry out]
Isn't that beautiful, Carla?
Breathtaking!
They call it Mercurius,
the luminaria flower palace.
Looking at it makes me
wonder what the king is like!
[WENDY] I bet he
has a long, white, beard.
[CARLA] Perhaps he does, child.
[LUCY]
It's really amazing how many
flowers there are in
the city, dontcha think?
[HAPPY] Well, they
don't call Crocus the
Flower-Blooming
Capital for nothin'!
[MALE CITIZEN 155E] A fight!
[NATSU] Ah!
I guess fights are part
of this festival after all!
Let's check it out!
[HAPPY] With all the
different guilds that are here,
there was bound to
be a couple of scuffles!
[LUCY] Hold on, you guys!
You smell that?
What is it?
It smells like there's
a dragon around here.
No way!
[NATSU] Move it!
Comin' through!
Anybody else want some?
[LECTOR] Man, these guys are
a nothin' but a bunch of losers!
[FROSCH] Yeah,
they're big-time losers!
[NATSU] What's goin' on?
Looky here.
Is that Natsu Dragneel?
Kitties?
Get a load of the stupid
lookin' blue pussycat.
He's stupid.
And they can talk, too!
[LUCY] And that's
surprising, why exactly?
[NATSU] Yeah,
that's me, but who are you?
Has this guy
seriously never heard
of Sting and Rogue,
the Twin Dragons of the
Sabertooth guild before?
They're the main force behind
the strongest guild in Fiore!
[LUCY] These guys are
members of Sabertooth?
You think you're hot stuff?
[Sting laughs]
So the rumors about you
entering the Grand Magic
Games this year
were true after all!
[NATSU]
How do you know who I am?
Everybody knows.
You're the so-called
Dragon Slayer
who couldn't actually
slay a dragon!
Doesn't sound like much
of a Dragon Slayer to me.
The sad part of it is...
I actually used to
look up to you.
And my friend was
a big fan of Gajeel's.
It was more of a curiosity,
as he was known
as a fellow Dragon Slayer.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
You're both Dragon Slayers?
[STING] We would
prefer that you call us
true Dragon Slayers instead.
Because unlike you, we could've
easily slain Acnologia.
Well you'd be telling
a different story if you had
actually gone up against
that monster like we did.
Yeah,
you weren't even there!
[LECTOR] This pussycat
sounds as dumb as he looks.
[FROSCH] Yeah, you're
way smarter than him, Lector!
[ROGUE] It doesn't matter
if we were there or not.
[STING] What it all boils
down to is we're far superior.
Let me explain a
little somethin' to ya.
Natsu and those
other two are what's
known as First-Generation
Dragon Slayers, cause they
all got their magic power
directly from dragons firsthand.
Your old buddy Loxus
and that guy Cobra
from the Oracion Seis
got their magic from dragon
lacrimas that were
implanted inside their bodies.
We call 'em second-generation
Dragon Slayers.
But Sting and Rogue
here are way more powerful,
cause not only do they have
dragon lacrimas inside 'em,
they were also raised
by actual dragons
who taught them
how to use their magic.
So they're
Third-Generation hybrids!
Third-Generation?
In other words, they're
the ultimate Dragon Slayers!
You guys really think you're so
much better than everyone else?
They don't just think they are,
there's a huge difference
in skill between first and
third gen Dragon Slayers.
You wish you were
half as strong as they are.
Tell me somethin'
did you guys'
dragons disappear in
the year 777, too?
Yeah, you could say that.
More to
the point, they died.
The creatures that passed
down their Dragon Slayer
magic techniques to us,
we eliminated them
with our own hands.
So that we could earn the
title of True Dragon Slayers.
I don't believe it.
You killed them?
Is that really true?
Humans killing Dragons.
You scum.
Those were your parents!
They're late.
Explain yourselves.
Where have you
been all this time?
[GRAY] Having a completely
un-enjoyable meal.
[LUCY] We ran into a
couple of other contestants.
A real nasty pair if you ask me.
Listen...
If you're somehow able to make
it past the qualifying rounds.
We'll give you a taste of what
true Dragon Slayer
magic feels like.
[ROGUE] Let's get going.
We're wasting our time
with this old generation scum.
It makes sense that these
old school Dragon Slayers
would drag around this kind of
litter box trash with 'em, huh?
Yeah, he's straight
outta the litter box!
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Those stupid jerks are gonna
wish they had never
messed with me!
Do any of you know
where Wendy ran off to?
[LUCY] Uh, no.
[GRAY] I haven't seen her.
Well it's a pretty safe
bet that she's off somewhere
with Carla, and it's not
really like her to get lost.
[ERZA] It's almost midnight.
[LUCY] I hate thinking
about a little girl like her
wandering around
the city at this hour.
[LUCY] Up all night.
Bad company.
Delinquency?
We're totally runnin'
things in this city now.
Don't screw with us!
[LUCY] What are we gonna do?
I know you're supposed
to be a writer and all,
but this isn't one
of your stories, Lucy.
We brought some supplies to
get you through the tournament.
Tomorrow's gonna
be a big day!
[GRAY]
Aw, thanks a lot you guys!
Hey, did you come
all the way here to
watch us beat up
on those other guilds?
[ELFMAN] Yeah.
I mean, I originally
wanted to get in on
the action and
impress my sisters.
[ELFMAN] But a real
man knows when to quit!
[ERZA] This is perfect timing.
Do you mind doing
us a small favor?
What do you need?
Well It's just that
Wendy hasn't made
it back here for
the night as of yet.
And those of us competing
in the games should
probably hang out here until
it turns twelve o' clock.
[LISANNA]
What happens at twelve?
We're not really sure
what, but the rules say
that we all hafta be
back here at midnight.
[GRAY] Which is right now.
[NATSU] What's gonna happen?
[MATO] Attention,
all contestants participating
in this year's Grand
Magic Games!
Good morning!
Outside!
Whoa, what in
the heck is that thing?
Is it some kinda hologram?
It's a great big pumpkin!
[MATO] To narrow down the one
hundred thirteen guilds in this
year's games to a
more manageable eight,
let's begin the
preliminary round!
Seriously?
Well, this is news!
Has there been a preliminary
round in years past?
No. This is completely new.
So this must
be the reason why we
were required to take
our places at midnight.
One hundred
and thirteen guilds,
narrowed down to a meager
eight in one fell swoop.
[LUCY THINKS] One hundred
thirteen. I had no idea there
were even that many guilds
in Fiore to begin with.
That number seems way too high.
[ERZA THINKS]
It doesn't make sense.
Why would they keep
this preliminary round
a secret until now?
Why all these new procedures?
[ERZA] The excessive
number of guilds involved.
And the mysterious magic
power Jellal talked about.
What are the organizers up to?
[MATO] Although the
number of guilds
increase and multiply each year.
"The games have gotten
boring now," is all I ever hear!
"Let's whittle them down"
I say to you!
And give just eight a cheer!
[MATO] The rules for this
preliminary round are simple!
[GRAY] What the--?
What's happening?
The inn is rising up!
[GRAY] Look! The other
ones are doin' it too!
[ELFMAN] A real man
dreams of rising up!
[MATO] Now, you will all
be participating in a race!
[MATO] The finish line is
at the Domus Flau coliseum!
Only the first eight teams
to reach it will move on
to the Grand Magic Games!
[GRAY] That's a path!
[ERZA] I suppose
we'll be following it?
[MATO] You're free to use
magic in any way you see fit!
There are no restrictions.
But remember,
only the first eight teams
to reach the finish
line will clear this round!
[MATO] However,
all five team members must
cross the goal for it to count!
[MATO] One more thing.
We are not responsible
for any loss of life that
may occur in the labyrinth.
Say what?
[MATO] So without further ado,
let the Grand Magic
Games' preliminary round,
Sky Labyrinth begin!
♪
[NATSU] Whoa!
What in the heck is that thing?
[HAPPY]
It's a big ol' floating maze.
But more importantly, it's where
the prelims are bein' held.
[NATSU] Aw man, I suck at mazes!
[HAPPY] Only the first
eight teams to reach the
goal get to compete
in the games!
[NATSU] So it's a race?
[HAPPY] Yeah, but all
five members of the
team have to get there to win!
[NATSU] Crap!
Wendy's still not here!
[HAPPY AND NATSU]
Next time: Sky Labyrinth!
[HAPPY] You know, I could take
Wendy's place if you need me to.
[NATSU] Awesome!
Elfman says
he'll fill in for her!
[HAPPY] Oh, he will?
Yeah, awesome.