- THE SKY ABOVE,
HOW LONELY AND
SORROWFUL IT SEEMS.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
- ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
- ♪ OH, BABY,
YEAH, YEAH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ MY PERFECT DREAM! ♪
- Chorus: ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ THE ROCK CITY BOY ♪
♪ BOY, BOY, BOY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA BELIEVE
THE SING ON THE BEAT ♪
♪ MOST RECENTLY
IS LIKE RECESS TO ME ♪
♪ PRETTY, PRETTY PLEASE,
NO BIRDS AND THE BEES ♪
♪ BUT ECSTASY
WITH EXTRA CHEESE ♪
♪ RHYMING RHINO
SOUNDING LIKE BONO ♪
♪ ALL SMACKED UP WITH
A BLACK JACK BOTTLE ♪
♪ WHEN I SAY "HO,"
YOU SAY "HEY"... ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
BACK IN THE WORLD OF EDOLAS,
THE TOWNSPEOPLE HAVE
BEGUN REBUILDING.
- HEY, WE'RE GONNA NEED
SOME MORE BRICKS OVER HERE.
- WE SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
FAUST WAS CALLED
THE DARK KING, AFTER ALL.
- YEAH, I DIDN'T EXPECT
THIS MUCH DAMAGE.
- HELL YEAH.
- LET'S NOT FIGHT.
WE NEED TO FOCUS
ON REBUILDING, OKAY?
- HE'S RIGHT.
IT MIGHT BE A LITTLE HARDER
WITHOUT MAGIC,
BUT WE CAN DO IT.
ARE YOU WITH ME?
- Men: YEAH!
- THINGS ARE STARTING
TO LOOK UP AROUND HERE.
- ( Happy speaking )
- I BROUGHT THE PRISONERS.
- Lucy: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
YOU GOT TO
BE KIDDING ME!
- WHAT? DO I LOOK
LIKE I'M KIDDING?
- I KNOW I ASKED YOU TO COME UP
WITH A CREATIVE WAY
FOR US TO BE ABLE THE GUILD
FROM PLACE TO PLACE...
BUT WHAT THE HECK
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
- YOU DON'T REALLY EXPECT US
TO PULL IT AROUND, DO YOU?
- LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY MORE
MAGIC POWER, REMEMBER?
- THOUGHT YOU COULD
SNEAK AWAY, DID YOU?
- NO, I, UH--
HEY, WAIT, I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WE COULD TOW IT
WITH MY MAGIC MOBILE.
MY MACHINE HAS GOT
SOME SERIOUS POWER.
I'M A FREAKING GENIUS.
OH YEAH!
GO FIRE!
- ( honks )
- UH-OH.
- WHY IS HE HAVING
TROUBLE WITH IT?
- BECAUSE HE'S AN IDIOT
WHO DOESN'T REALIZE
THAT YOU CAN'T START UP
A MAGIC MOBILE
WITHOUT MAGIC POWER.
- YOU'RE AS SMART
AS YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL.
- SPEAKING OF IDIOTS,
WOULD YOU LAY OFF?
- THAT WAS MEAN.
- I'M SORRY, LUCY.
- I HAD A FEELING YOU
WERE GONNA SCREW UP.
- THAT'S MEAN!
- LISTEN UP, THE GUILD HALL
ISN'T GONNA DRAG ITSELF
TO ROYAL CITY.
EVERYONE TO YOUR POSITIONS.
- YEAH!
- Men: HEAVE HO!
HEAVE HO!
- YOU READY? LET'S GO?
- Men: HEAVE HO!  HEAVE HO!
- Mirajane: OKAY.
- HEAVE HO! HEAVE HO!
- ( groaning )
- EXCUSE ME, WHY AREN'T
YOU LADIES HELPING?
- HOW RUDE!
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER
THAN TO ASK
DELICATE MAIDENS LIKE US
TO HAUL THAT THING.
- WHAT?! DELICATE MAIDENS?!
YOU?!
- EDOLAS'S ROYAL CITY
HAS ENTERED A NEW ERA.
IT'S PEOPLE ARE NOW
LOOKING FORWARD TO THE FUTURE.
HOWEVER, THEY HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
THE PAIN AND TROUBLE
YOU'VE CAUSED THEM
IN THE PAST.
THEREFORE, YOU MUST BE GIVEN
DUE PUNISHMENT FOR YOUR ACTIONS.
- YES, WE UNDERSTAND.
- AS THE NEW KING,
I HEREBY PROCLAIM,
SIR FAUST, YOU'RE PERMANENTLY
EXILED FROM THE KINGDOM.
YOU ARE PROHIBITED
FROM EVER SETTING FOOT
IN THE ROYAL CITY AGAIN.
- ( sighs )
- THE POOR GUY.
- ERZA KNIGHTWALKER,
YOU CANNOT LEAVE THE KINGDOM
UNLESS I'VE AUTHORIZED YOU
TO DO SO.
- I'M PREPARED TO DIE
FOR MY SINS.
YOU NEEDN'T HOLD BACK.
- I'M NOT.
I ORDER YOU
TO HELP THE CITIZENS
REBUILD THE ROYAL CITY.
- ( gasps )
- BYRO, SUGARBOY, HUGHES,
YOU ARE ALL GIVEN THE SAME
PUNISHMENT AS KNIGHTWALKER.
- ( all gasp )
- CARE TO EXPLAIN YOURSELF?
- YEAH, THIS IS,
LIKE, AWESOME,
BUT IT'S ALSO
TOTALLY MESSED UP.
- HMM.
SO THE MAGIC WARFARE UNITS
DON'T GET THE FULL BRUNT?
- I'M AFRAID I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE HOPING TO ACHIEVE.
- YOUR ATONEMENT,
NOTHING MORE.
- WELL, THEN YOU SHOULD
SIMPLY EXECUTE US.
WE DON'T WANT TO LIVE
OUR LIVES IN DISGRACE.
- SERIOUSLY, IT'S NOT
A BIG DEAL.  JUST DO IT.
- IN FACT, WE WERE PREPARED
FOR THAT PUNISHMENT.
- OH, NEW KING,
THIS IS OUR DESIRE.
WON'T YOU PLEASE
SYMPATHIZE WITH OUR FEELINGS
AND GRANT US
THIS ONE LAST WISH?
- VERY WELL.
- IF THEY'RE GONNA
GIVE THEIR LIVES TO ATONE,
THEN I WANT TO DO IT TOO.
- COCO, NO.
I CANNOT ALLOW THAT AFTER
YOU REFORMED OF YOUR OWN ACCORD.
THAT WAS TRULY NOBLE OF YOU.
DON'T LET YOUR PAST OVERSHADOW
SUCH AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
- I WON'T.
- I KNOW THAT EVEN
WITHOUT MAGIC POWER,
EACH OF YOU POSSESSES
AMAZING INNATE ABILITIES,
NOT TO MENTION WISDOM
AND EXPERIENCE.
WE NEED YOUR HELP
TO REBUILD THE ROYAL CITY.
HOWEVER, IF YOU INSIST
THAT YOU CANNOT BEAR IT,
I WILL GRANT YOU THE ULTIMATE
PUNISHMENT YOU DESIRE.
- THE SAME SHOULD GO
FOR HIS HIGHNESS.
EXCUSE ME.
THE SAME SHOULD GO
FOR SIR, FAUST.
I THINK THAT'S THE ONLY
FAIR SOLUTION, DON'T YOU?
- SHE'S GOT
A PRETTY GOOD POINT.
- MY PUNISHMENT IS FAIR.
- HMM?!
- BUT, SIR!
- TAKE CARE OF YOURSELVES.
I AM GRATEFUL TO YOU,
THE NEW KING,
FOR SHOWING SUCH MERCY.
BEFORE HE LEFT OUR WORLD,
I CALLED OUT
TO THAT YOUNG MAN.
- YES, I'M AWARE OF THAT.
- SOLIDARITY...
- HUH?
- CONVICTION, AND COURAGE.
IT WOULD APPEAR I'VE FORGOTTEN
WHAT IS TRULY IMPORTANT IN LIFE.
BEING IN A GUILD,
DO YOU ENJOY IT?
- YEAH!
- Faust: I UNDERSTAND WHY.
IT'S SOMETHING
I WILL NEVER FORGET--
THE WAY HE SMILED WHEN
I ASKED HIM THAT QUESTION.
IT STIRRED
SOMETHING WITHIN ME.
I SUPPOSE THIS IS GOOD-BYE.
COCO, DON'T EVER
STOP RUNNING, CHILD.
- ( gasps )
I WON'T!
( cries )
- ( classical music plays )
- ( sighs )
MAN, THIS IS THE LIFE,
AIN'T IT?
- THIS TEA IS DELICIOUS.
- ABOUT TIME
WE GOT TO RELAX.
- Men: ARE YOU HAVING
A TEA PARTY IN THERE?!
COME OUT HERE
AND HELP US!
- ( chirps )
- GOOD JOB, GUYS!
- ( groans ) - WE MADE
IT TO OUR DESTINATION!
- Men: YEAH,
NO THANKS TO YOU.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD?
- IT SEEMS THEY DRAGGED
THAT BUILDING
ALL THE WAY HERE.
- I'VE SEEN THAT SYMBOL
BEFORE SOMEWHERE.
- PEOPLE OF THE ROYAL CITY...
- Juvia: HI.
- Juvia and Wendy: WE'RE MEMBERS
OF THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
- WE CAN SOLVE ANY PROBLEMS
THAT YOU MAY HAVE.
- AND NOBODY CAN
BEAT OUR PRICES.
- WE'RE RUNNING A SPECIAL
FOR OUR GRAND OPENING
SO ACT NOW.
- STOP ON BY!
- WOW, THAT'S GREAT!
- MY ROOF WAS DAMAGED
DURING THE MESS
WITH THE DARK LORD.
- WE'RE GONNA NEED
MORE BRICK LAYERS
IF WE'RE GONNA REBUILD THE CITY.
WOULD YOU LEND US A HAND?
- WE'D LOVE TO.
- I DON'T THE FIRST THING
ABOUT FIXING ROOFS.
- ME NEITHER, OR LAYING BRICKS.
- OH, MAN.
- WELL, LET'S GO.
- Male Fairy Members:
HOW CAN YOU BE SO CRUEL?!
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
BACK IN EARTH LAND,
FAIRY TALE IS
IN FOR A SURPRISE.
- ( gasping )
- Narrator: AND ELSEWHERE...
- ( chatter )
- BUT I THOUGHT
WE'D LOST YOU.
- SO YOU WERE ALIVE
ALL ALONG?
- ( overlapping chatter )
- HM-HMM.
- ( stampeding feet )
- ( gasps )
- LISANNA!
- KEEP YOUR FILTHY PAWS
OFF OF HER.
- I THINK THEY'RE JUST
HAPPY TO SEE HER, MAN.
- YEAH, CHILL OUT.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
- IT'S SUCH A RELIEF
TO SEE THE GUILD
BACK TO HOW IT WAS BEFORE.
- YEAH, NO JOKE.
IT SEEMS LIKE THEY
DON'T HAVE A CLUE
ABOUT THE ANIMA STUFF.
- I'M JUST GLAD
TO SEE THEY'RE SAFE
AND SOUND.
- PRETTY CRAZY, AIN'T IT?
- SO THIS IS WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE IN A GUILD.
- LISANNA.
- MASTER.
- I WAS SO WORRIED.
I CONSIDER THOSE WHO'VE BEEN
RAISED BY THIS GUILD
MY OWN CHILDREN.
- ( gasps ) - EVERY PARENT
WORRIES ABOUT THEIR CHILDREN.
AND EVERY PARENT HAS FAITH
IN THEIR CHILDREN.
YOU CAN FILL ME IN
ON ALL THE DETAILS ANOTHER TIME.
SAME FOR THE REST OF YOU.
- OKAY, SURE THING, GRAMPS.
- TODAY, WE'LL ALL CELEBRATE
YOUR RETURN TO FAIRY TAIL!
- OH, THANK YOU.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'VE COME HOME.
AND I'LL NEVER LEAVE AGAIN.
- YOU CAN, CHILD.
FOR NO MATTER WHERE YOU GO,
THIS WILL ALWAYS BE HOME.
WELCOME BACK, LISANNA DEAR.
- All: WELCOME BACK, LISANNA!
( scattered laughing,
cheering )
- ( cries )
THANK YOU, MASTER!
- ( whimpers )
SHE TACKLED HIM.
- BE CAREFUL.
THE MASTER'S FRAGILE.
- ( cries )
- WELL, GET IT OUT, CHILD,
BEFORE THE PARTY BEGINS.
- All: CHEERS!
- OKAY, WHO'S READY
FOR ANOTHER ROUND?
- OVER HERE, KINANA.
- I COULD USE ANOTHER ONE TOO.
- TAKE A BREAK AND
COME PARTY WITH US.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MUCH
EVERYBODY'S CHANGED.
- ALTHOUGH, I'D SAY
YOU'VE CHANGED THE MOST, MIRA.
- WHO ME?
- BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
'CAUSE IT'S STILL
THE SAME FAIRY TAIL
I REMEMBER.
- Fried: LISANNA.
- THIS IS A ROCKING DAY, BABIES.
- Tommens: OH YEAH!
- I'M GLAD YOU MADE IT HOME
IN ONE PIECE.
- YES, WELCOME BACK, LISANNA.
- THE THUNDER LEGION!
I NEVER EXPECTED
TO SEE YOU HERE.
- WELL, I CAN UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'D BE SURPRISED,
BUT CONSIDER
THE GUILD'S NAME.
RIGHT? "FAIRY."
I'M THE MOST FAIRY-LIKE.
- IS IT JUST ME OR
IS HER HAIR DIFFERENT?
- GLOOMY.
- WHOA!
JUVIA'S IS TOO.
- IS THAT RAIN?
- GLOOMY. - I WONDER
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO HER?
- SHE CERTAINLY DOESN'T
SEEM VERY HAPPY.
- GLOOMY.
- THINGS ARE DIFFERENT
IN EDOLAS.
CAN YOU BELIEVE
GRAY'S THE ONE IN LOVE WITH YOU?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
- MAYBE IT'S YOUR HAIRSTYLE.
- YOU SHOULD SEE
THE OTHER-WORLD YOU.
( chuckles ) JUST THE THOUGHT
THAT MAKES ME CRACK UP.
- COME ON, WOULD YOU JUST
SPILL IT ALREADY?
I'D LIKE TO GET BACK
TO DRINKING.
- ( laughing )
- Juvia: I WANT TO GO
TO THIS EDOLAS PLACE.
- OKAY, I GET IT NOW.
- I'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- I LOVE BEING IN A GUILD!
DON'T YOU, HAPPY?!
- AYE, AYE, SIR!
- HEY, PIPE DOWN.
- YEAH, QUIT BUSTING UP
THE PLACE.
- I WONDER IF THE OTHER NATSU
IS AS CRAZY AS OURS IS.
- IF SO, I FEEL REALLY BAD
FOR HIS GUILD.
- ACTUALLY,
HE'S MORE LIKE THIS.
- WHY YOU
SO MEAN TO ME, LUCY?
WHAT'D I DO TO YOU?
- ( laughing )
- HE'S A WIMP.
- WOW, NO WAY.
- WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE
TO MEET NATSU THE CRYBABY!
- MY TUMMY HURTS FROM LAUGHING!
- THAT'S HILARIOUS!
- QUIT LAUGHING
AT THE OTHER ME
RIGHT NOW!
- SORRY, BUT
I THINK IT'S CUTE.
- YO, HAPPY, I HEAR
YOU WERE KICKING BUTT
OVER IN EDOLAS.
- AYE.
NOT TO CHANGE THE SUBJECT,
BUT AS YOU CAN SEE
THERE'S A DRAGON SLAYER
WHO'S SO EXCITED
HE'S GONE ON A RAMPAGE.
WOULD YOU MIND KNOCKING
SOME SENSE INTO HIM?
- YEAH, SURE, BUT LET'S
WAIT TILL THE PARTY'S OVER.
- I GUESS THAT'S WHAT
YOU'D CALL TOUGH LOVE?
- SCREW WAITING
TILL IT'S OVER, GILDARTS!
WHY DON'T
YOU FIGHT ME NOW--
( groans )
- GEEZ, THEY CERTAINLY
ARE A ROWDY BUNCH, AREN'T THEY?
- I THINK THAT'S MOST
PEOPLE'S FIRST IMPRESSION
OF FAIRY TAIL.
- THERE'S NEVER A DULL MOMENT.
- SO EVERYONE HERE POSSESSES
A MAGIC POWER OF SOME SORT?
( gulps )
- THAT'S CORRECT.
THE SAME HOLDS TRUE
FOR ALL EARTH LAND WIZARDS.
- ERZA.
- I ALMOST FORGOT
THAT YOU WORKED WITH
THE LESS THAN PLEASANT
ERZA KNIGHTWALKER
BACK IN EDOLAS.
- YOU'RE GONNA LIKE OURS BETTER.
- HOWEVER, I DON'T THINK
THE MAGIC ITSELF
IS WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT.
I BELIEVE IT IS THE HEARTS
OF THOSE WHO WIELD IT.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE, LILY?
- HMPH, YOU MAY BE
A DIFFERENT PERSON,
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT
I FIND IT COMFORTING
TO HAVE A FAMILIAR FACE AROUND.
- I'VE GOT A WAGER FOR YOU
AND THE LITTLE GIRL, SALAMANDER!
I BETCHA MY LILY
CAN BEAT THE EVER-LOVING CRAP
OUT OF YOUR PUNY CATS!
- YEAH?
- ( laughs )
- YOUR KITTY UP
TO THE CHALLENGE?
- LOOKS LIKE THE BIG GUY'S
GOT HIS HEART SET
ON HAVING THEM FIGHT.
- UH-HUH.
- DON'T WORRY.
SHE CAN HANDLE HIM.  I THINK.
- GO AHEAD AND
MAKE MY DAY, YOU PUNK.
- I WILL.
- DO WE HAVE ANY SAY?
- AIN'T NO WAY YOU GUYS
CAN BEAT MY LILY.
HE'S THE STRONGEST
WITH A CAPITAL "S."
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT
BECAUSE HAPPY'S A CAT
WITH A LOWER CASE "C."
- UH, NATSU,
YOU KNOW I DON'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST HIM.
- NOW, DON'T SELL
YOURSELF SHORT, HAPPY,
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP
WHEN YOU HAVEN'T EVEN TRIED.
- ( gasps )
YOU MEAN IT?
YOU REALLY THINK
I GOT A SHOT?
- NOW HOLD ON.
DESPITE MY CURRENT APPEARANCE,
I WAS A DIVISION COMMANDER
BACK IN EDOLAS.
IF WE WERE TO FIGHT,
YOU COULD BE SERIOUSLY INJURED.
- YOU'VE GOT A GOOD POINT.
- I MUST SAY THAT
WAS QUITE MATURE OF YOU.
- IT JUST SEEMS THAT WAY
BECAUSE THEY'RE CHILDISH.
WELL, I FOR ONE HOPE
THAT THE THREE OF US
CAN BE FRIENDS FROM NOW ON.
- AYE, SIR.
- FINE.
- ( sighs )
- WOULD SOMEONE CARE TO EXPLAIN
WHY ALL THE BOYS ARE FIGHTING?
- EVIDENTLY, GRAY AND ELFMAN
GOT DRAGGED INTO IT TOO.
- FLESH STRIKING FLESH
REPEATEDLY WITH FORCE.
- I'LL JOIN YOU!
- NO, DON'T STRIP.
- I SUPPOSE THAT
I SHOULD TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE CHANCE TO LET LOOSE.
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- IF YOU GUYS ARE GOING IN,
THEN I AM TOO.
- THEY NEED TO CALM DOWN.
THIS IS GETTING OUT OF HAND.
- WELL, GET USED TO IT
BECAUSE IT HAPPENS A LOT.
- IT'S PART OF WHAT MAKES
FAIRY TAIL SO MUCH FUN.
- ( giggles )
- Makarov: LET ME ASK YOU
SOMETHING, NATSU.
WHAT WAS I LIKE IN THIS
OTHER WORLD YOU VISITED?
- YOU MEAN,
THE EDOLAS VERSION OF YOU?
- Makarov:
YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT HIM.
WAS HE THE OPPOSITE OF ME?
- Natsu: WELL, NOW THAT
I THINK ABOUT IT--
NO WAY.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THERE WAS
SOMETHING ABOUT THE OLD GUY
THAT SEEMED
KIND OF FAMILIAR.
HA! THAT'S IT!
- WHAT'S WHAT?
- Both: BEING IN A GUILD,
DO YOU ENJOY IT?
- I'M NOT TOTALLY SURE,
BUT I THINK YOU MIGHT
HAVE BEEN THE KING.
- OH, YEAH?
HMM.
- HEY, SO WHAT WAS I LIKE
OVER THERE?
WAS I A DASHING PRINCE
OR A GREAT SOLDIER?
- ACTUALLY,
I DON'T REMEMBER
SEEING ANYBODY THERE
WHO LOOKED LIKE YOU.
I GUESS IT'S POSSIBLE
YOU WERE A FROG OR
FISH OR SOMETHING.
- NOT FUNNY, NATSU!
- ( laughs )
- AREN'T YOU THE ONE
THAT STARTED THIS, PYRO?
- BETTER HURRY AND
GET OVER HERE OR ELSE!
- YEAH, COME FIGHT US
LIKE A REAL MAN!
- ONLY A COWARD
WOULD TURN THEIR BACK
ON A FIGHT THEY INITIATED.
WE'RE FINALLY SEEING
THE SALAMANDER'S TRUE COLOR--
- SHUT UP, LOSER!
- YUP, SAW THAT COMING.
( chuckles )
GILDARTS, TELL ME SOMETHING.
- HMM?
- DO YOU THINK MYSTOGAN'S
GONNA BE OKAY OVER IN EDOLAS?
I DON'T WANT TO SOUND
LIKE AN OLD FOOL,
BUT I CAN'T HELP BUT WORRY
ABOUT MY CHILDREN.
- I'M SURE HE'LL BE FINE.
AFTER ALL, HE GREW UP
IN THIS GUILD.
HE'LL ALWAYS BE ONE OF US.
- HMM.
( chuckles )
SO HOW LONG YOU PLANNING
TO STAY IN TOWN THIS TIME?
- Gildarts: WELL,
I HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
- Makarov: THERE'S SOMETHING
I'D LIKE TO DISCUSS WITH YOU.
- Gildarts: YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
WHY SO FORMAL?
- Narrator:
THIS BIZARRE BUILDING
SERVES AS THE HEADQUARTERS
OF THE NEWLY REFORMED
MAGIC COUNCIL.
- THIS IS DISGRACEFUL.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SO MANY
INCIDENT REPORTS.
- Council Member #1:
IT IS ALARMING
ESPECIALLY SINCE
THEY'RE THE RESULT
OF A SINGLE GUILD'S
INDISCRETIONS .
- Council Member #2:
FAIRY TAIL.
THEY CAUSED
PLENTY OF HEADACHES
FOR OUR PREDECESSORS.
- WHILE THEY CAN
BE TROUBLESOME,
THEY'RE NOT DESERVING
OF SUCH CRITICISM.
AFTER ALL, WE OWE THEM FOR
WIPING OUT THE ORACION SEIS
AND THE BARAM ALLIANCE.
- WE OWE THEM?!
THAT'S THE MOST RIDICULOUS THING
I'VE EVER HEARD, MASTER ORG.
- I'M AFRAID THAT
THERE IS NO RECORD
OF THE MAGIC COUNCIL EVER
APPROVING THEIR OPERATION.
- AS FAR AS WE CAN TELL,
IT WAS SIMPLY A BAND
OF LOCAL GUILDS ACTING
OF THEIR OWN ACCORD.
- AND TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE,
EVEN THOUGH THEY DECLARED WAR
AGAINST A DARK GUILD,
THEIR ACTIONS PUT THEM
IN VIOLATION
OF THE INTER-GUILD
CONFLICT-BAN TREATY.
- I WORRY THAT THIS INCIDENT
COULD MOTIVATE
THE BARAM ALLIANCE TO RETALIATE
AGAINST THE OFFICIAL GUILDS.
- I DON'T THINK THERE
IS CAUSE FOR CONCERN.
THE LIGHT TEAM CALLED THEMSELVES
AN ALLIANCE AS WELL.
BUT THEY WERE JUST PART
OF A NON-AGGRESSION TREATY.
- HMM.
- Council Member #3:
CONCERNING JELLAL
WHO WAS CAPTURED
IN THE WORTH WOODSEA?
- WE'VE RECEIVED REPORTS
THAT THERE ARE MEMBERS
OF THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD
WHO'VE GONE SO FAR
AS TO REFER TO HIM
AS ONE OF THEIR OWN.
- IF THAT'S TRUE,
ARE WE SURE THEY CAN BE TRUSTED?
- CAN'T YOU SEE? THIS IS OUR
CHANCE TO ASSERT OURSELVES!
LET'S SHOW THE OTHER GUILDS
WE WON'T PUT UP
WITH THIS KIND OF BEHAVIOR.
- CHAIRMAN, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- IF WE ARE TO REGAIN THE TRUST
THE OLD COUNCIL SQUANDERED,
THEN WE MUST CRACK DOWN
ON THE PROBLEMATIC GUILDS.
FAIRY TAIL WON'T
GET ANOTHER CHANCE.
ONE MORE INCIDENT
AND THEY'RE DISBANDED.
- Narrator:
THIS MAN IS CHAIRMAN
OF THE NEW MAGIC COUNCIL.
HIS NAME IS GRAN DOMA.
- HMM.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, ORG?
ARE YOU DISSATISFIED?
- NO, SIR.
- I'M AMAZED
BY YOUR NAIVETE.
TO THINK YOU WERE THOROUGHLY
FOOLED BY A PROJECTION.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND HOW
INCREDIBLY RECKLESS IT WAS
TO ALLOW THE R-SYSTEM
TO BE ACTIVATED?
- I DO, SIR.
- SUMMON THEM.
- Org: YES, CHAIRMAN.
LAHAR AND DORANBOLT,
COME TO THE COUNCIL AT ONCE!
- WE UPHOLD THE SANCTITY
OF ORDER IN THE MAGIC WORLD!
- Council members:
FOR THE SANCTITY OF ORDER.
- WHOA.
LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE
DID SOME SERIOUS PARTYING.
- ( snoring )
- I'M SO HAPPY
FOR MIRA AND ELFMAN.
- ( snores )
( grumbles )
- Lucy: I BET NATSU WISHES
HE COULD BE REUNITED
WITH IGNEEL.
SOMETIMES I WONDER
IF HE EVER FEELS SAD OR LONELY.
- ( giggles )
- YOU KNOW, HE'S KIND OF CUTE
WHEN HE'S SLEEPING.
- FIRE.
- HMM?
FIRE-- FIRE.
- ( giggles )
- ( thudding )
- FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST.
- ( screams )
- ( giggles )
TOLD YOU NOT TO
BACK TALK TO ME, GRAY.
- WHY AM I NOT SURPRISED?
- ( growling )
- PLEASE, YOU MUSTN'T
COME NEAR ME.
NO, STAY BACK.
I'M NOT YOUR ENEMY.
I MEAN YOU NO HARM.
- ( growling )
- I TRIED TO WARN YOU.
I TOLD YOU TO STAY AWAY.
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T MEAN TO TAKE
THE LIVES OF OTHERS.
IT'S AS THOUGH
THE WORLD IS REJECTING ME.
- NATSU.
I HOPE THAT
I WILL SEE YOU SOON.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: WHAT THE HECK?
HAVE YOU SEEN MY SCARF?
- Happy: YEAH,
IT'S ON THE BED.
- WHAT ABOUT MY SHIRT?
- IT'S DRYING OUTSIDE.
- AND MY UNDERWEAR?
- YOU'RE WEARING 'EM.
- ( laughs )
WHAT WOULD I DO WITHOUT YOU?
YOU'RE THE BEST, HAPPY.
- YEAH, YEAH.
WOULD YOU JUST HURRY
AND GET DRESSED ALREADY?
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR OUR JOB!
- YOU KNOW WHAT YOU AND I ARE,
LITTLE BUDDY?
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY
TO DESCRIBE US.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I USUALLY FEEL
MORE LIKE YOUR NANNY
THAN I DO YOUR PARTNER.