- Narrator: IN A LAND
FAR, FAR AWAY
LIES THE KINGDOM
OF FIORE,
A SMALL, PEACEFUL NATION
OF 17 MILLION,
AND A PLACE FILLED
WITH MAGIC.
FOUND IN EVERY HOME,
BOUGHT AND SOLD
IN EVERY MARKETPLACE.
FOR MOST MAGIC IS
MERELY A TOOL,
A MUNDANE PART
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
FOR SOME, HOWEVER,
MAGIC IS AN ART,
AND THEY'VE DEVOTED
THEIR LIVES TO ITS PRACTICE.
THESE ARE THE WIZARDS.
BANDED TOGETHER INTO
MAGICAL GUILDS,
THEY PLY THEIR SKILLS
IN SEARCH OF FAME AND FORTUNE.
MANY SUCH GUILDS DOT
THE LANDSCAPE OF FIORE.
BUT THERE IS A CERTAIN GUILD
IN A CERTAIN TOWN
THAT SOARS HIGH
ABOVE THE REST.
ONE FROM WHICH COUNTLESS LEGENDS
HAVE BEEN BORN.
A GUILD THAT WILL NO DOUBT
CONTINUE TO CREATE LEGENDS
WELL INTO THE FUTURE.
ITS NAME IS FAIRY TAIL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: ON THE LAST
EPISODE OF "FAIRY TAIL."
- WHAT?  YOU GUYS ARE
LOOKING FOR A FIRE DRAGON?
- I'M GONNA HURL.
- ( gasps )
YOU TRICKED ME!
- I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU DIRTY
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD'S NAME.
- HE OVERDID IT!
- YOU WANTED TO JOIN
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD,
DIDN'T YOU?
- Lucy: ALL RIGHT!
- Narrator:
THIS IS THE MAGIC COUNCIL, ERA.
- THOSE IDIOTS FROM FAIRY TAIL
HAVE GONE AND DONE IT AGAIN.
THIS TIME THEY'VE DESTROYED
AN ENTIRE PORT.
- WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH THEM?
- I'M ACTUALLY QUITE FOND
OF THOSE DIMWITS
AND THEIR LAISSEZ-FAIRE
ATTITUDE.
- HMM.  THEY MAY
BEHAVE LIKE FOOLS,
BUT WE MUSTN'T FORGET
THEY ARE ALSO
AN EXTREMELY CAPABLE LOT.
- Doma: YES, THAT'S TRUE.
THEY PRESENT QUITE THE QUANDARY.
- I THINK WE SHOULD
LEAVE THEM BE.
AFTER ALL, IF IT
WASN'T FOR THOSE FOOLS
THINK HOW BORING
THIS WORLD WOULD BE.
- Happy: WELCOME TO FAIRY TAIL!
- ( giggles )
- WE MADE IT BACK ALIVE!
- WE'RE HOME!
- ( laughing, chatter )
- ( chuckles )
- SO I HEARD YOU WENT ALL OUT
IN HARGEON, NATSU.
HAD TO GO STARTING TROU--
AAH!
- WHY DID YOU DO THAT?!
- YOU LIED ABOUT
THAT SALAMANDER.
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR BUTT.
- DON'T GET MAD AT ME.
I'M NOT THE ONE TO BLAME HERE.
I'M JUST PASSING ALONG
A RUMOR I HEARD.
- IT WAS JUST A RUMOR?!
- YOU WANT TO FIGHT?!
- LET'S GO!
- ( all shout )
- NOW NOW, NATSU,
I THINK YOU NEED
TO CALM DOWN--!
- OH, WOW.
I'M ACTUALLY STANDING INSIDE
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD HALL.
- SO NATSU FINALLY
MADE IT BACK, HUH?
- ( gasps )
- Narrator:
THIS IS GRAY FULLBUSTER.
A VERY TALENTED WIZARD,
BUT HE TENDS TO--
WELL, HE HAS A BAD HABIT
OF TAKING OFF HIS CLOTHES.
- IT'S TIME WE SETTLED THINGS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- GRAY, YOUR CLOTHES?
- I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THAT!
- Narrator: THIS LOVELY LADY
IS CANA ALBERONA.
SHE HOLDS THE TITLE
OF FAIRY TAIL'S
HEAVIEST DRINKER.
YOU SEE? I DON'T DATE THE MEN
HERE BECAUSE THEY HAVE NO CLASS.
- ( gasps )
- COME HERE AND FIGHT ME,
NATSU!
- NOT UNTIL YOU PUT
SOME CLOTHES ON.
- IT'S ONLY NOON
AND YOU BOYS ARE ALREADY
WHINING LIKE
SPOILED BABIES.
- Narrator: THIS BRUTE OF A MAN
IS ELFMAN,
A MUSCLE-BOUND WIZARD
WHO BELIEVES THAT ALL YOU NEED
TO SOLVE ANY PROBLEM
ARE TWO STRONG FISTS.
- ( grunts )
I'M A REAL MAN.
YOU WANT ME TO
PROVE IT TO YOU?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S ENCOURAGING THEM.
- ( both grunt )
- THEY KNOCKED HIM OUT
THAT EASILY?
( giggles ) - JEEZ, IT'S SO
NOISY AROUND HERE, HUH?
- ( girls sigh )
- WOW.
- Narrator: THIS IS
THE LADY-KILLER, LOKE.
RANKED HIGH ON THE MOST
ELIGIBLE WIZARD BACHELOR'S LIST.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M GONNA GO FIGHT,
ONLY TO PROTECT YOU TWO.
- Both: GOOD LUCK, LOKE.
- HE'S DEFINITELY
OFF MY LIST.
WHAT THE HECK IS WRONG
WITH THESE PEOPLE?
THERE'S NOT ONE SANE PERSON
IN THE WHOLE PLACE.
- Mirajane: HELLO.
ARE YOU NEW HERE?
- IT'S MIRAJANE
IN THE FLESH!
- ( giggles )
- Narrator:
THIS IS MIRAJANE.
A BEAUTIFUL WIZARD
WHO'S KNOWN FOR HER
BIKINI-CLAD PHOTO SPREADS
IN SORCERER WEEKLY MAGAZINE.
SHE'S CURRENTLY
AN EMPLOYEE AT FAIRY TAIL.
- UM, DON'T YOU THINK WE SHOULD
TRY TO STOP THEM OR SOMETHING?
- IT'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS
AROUND HERE.
I JUST LEAVE THEM ALONE.
BESIDES--
- AAH!
- IT'S KIND OF FUN,
DON'T YOU THINK?
( groans )
- ( screams )
DON'T DIE, MIRAJANE!
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
- GIVE ME BACK
MY UNDERWEAR, JERK!
- AAH!
- EXCUSE ME, MISS, COULD I
PLEASE BORROW YOUR UNDERWEAR?
- AS IF!
( gasps )
- THESE GUYS ARE ALL
SO INSENSITIVE.
A WOMAN HAS NEEDS.
( grunts )
- REAL MEN SPEAK WITH
THEIR FISTS, LOKE!
( shouts )
- I TOLD YOU TO BUTT OUT!
- AYE...
- IT'S SO LOUD.
SO MUCH FOR HAVING
A DRINK TO RELAX.
THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU GUYS.
I SUGGEST THAT YOU
KNOCK IT OFF.
- OH YEAH?
SAYS WHO?
- ( shouts )
- YOU PUNKS CAN BE
SUCH A NUISANCE.
- I'M READY FOR YA!
- THEY ALWAYS
FIGHT LIKE THIS?
- UH-HUH.
- YOU DON'T SEEM WORRIED.
- WOULD YOU FOOLS
STOP BICKERING LIKE CHILDREN?!
- HE'S HUGE!
- ( coughing )
- I'M SORRY.  I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE STILL HERE, MASTER.
- ( groans )
- DID YOU SAY MASTER?!
- ( laughs )
MAN, TALK ABOUT
A BUNCH OF BABIES.
LOOKS LIKE I WON
THIS ROUND, YOU GUYS.
- ( gasps )
- WELL, SEEMS WE'VE
A NEW RECRUIT.
- YES, SIR.
- ( grunts )
- ( whimpers )
( gasps )
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HE'S TINY.  THIS LITTLE GUY'S
REALLY IN CHARGE HERE?
- OF COURSE HE IS.
ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD MASTER,
MAKAROV.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- OOH!
( groans )
( clears throat )
YOU'VE GONE AND
DONE IT AGAIN,
YOU BUNCH OF CLODS.
JUST TAKE A LOOK AT
HOW MUCH PAPERWORK
THE MAGIC COUNCIL
SENT ME THIS TIME.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST
PILE OF COMPLAINTS YET.
- Narrator:
REMEMBER THE MAGIC COUNCIL?
WELL, THEY MONITOR ALL OF
THE DIFFERENT WIZARD GUILDS.
- HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MINDS?!
ALL YOU KIDS ARE GOOD FOR
IS GETTING THE HIGHER-UPS
MAD AT ME.
- ( all murmur )
- ( groans )
- ( exhales )
- HOWEVER...
I SAY TO HECK WITH
THE MAGIC COUNCIL.
( chuckles )
- ( gasps )
- Makarov: NOW LISTEN UP.
ANY POWER THAT SURPASSES REASON
STILL COMES FROM REASON,
RIGHT?
MAGIC ISN'T SOME KIND OF
MIRACULOUS POWER.
IT IS A TALENT
THAT ONLY WORKS
WHEN THE FLOW OF ENERGY
INSIDE OF US
AND THE FLOW OF ENERGY
IN THE NATURAL WORLD
ARE IN PERFECT
SYNCHRONIZATION.
TO PERFORM MAGIC,
ONE MUST HAVE A STRONG MIND
AND THE ABILITY TO FOCUS.
IT SHOULD TAKE OVER
YOUR BEING
AND COME POURING
OUT OF YOUR SOUL.
IF ALL WE DO IS WORRY
ABOUT FOLLOWING RULES,
THEN OUR MAGIC
WILL NEVER PROGRESS.
DON'T LET THOSE BLOWHARDS
ON THE COUNCIL SCARE YOU.
FOLLOW THE PATH
YOU BELIEVE IN.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT MAKES
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD
NUMBER ONE!
- ( cheering )
- YEAH!
- ( laughs )
- ( cuckoo clock ticking )
- AND THEN...
- THERE. NOW YOU'RE AN OFFICIAL
MEMBER OF THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD.
- ( gasps, squeals )
HEY, NATSU, LOOK.
MIRAJANE JUST PUT THE OFFICIAL
FAIRY TAIL MARK ON MY HAND!
- OH YEAH?  THAT'S COOL.
WELCOME TO THE GUILD, LOONY.
- THE NAME'S LUCY!
- Narrator:
THIS IS THE REQUEST BOARD.
THE WIZARDS CAN PICK
FROM ANY OF THE JOBS
LISTED ON THE BOARD.
EACH PRESENTS
A UNIQUE CHALLENGE,
AND A DIFFERENT PAY RATE.
- MAKE SURE YOU PICK ONE
WITH A BIG REWARD, NATSU.
- WHOA, 160,000 JEWEL
TO GET RID OF SOME THIEVES?
- Happy:
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME!
- Romeo: HOW COME MY DAD
HASN'T COME BACK YET?
- Makarov: YOU'RE STARTING
TO WORK MY NERVES, ROMEO.
YOU'RE A WIZARD, SON.
HAVE FAITH IN YOUR FATHER
AND WAIT PATIENTLY FOR HIM.
- BUT SIR, HE TOLD ME
HE'D BE BACK IN THREE DAYS.
AND HE'S BEEN GONE
FOR OVER A WEEK NOW!
- IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
HE TOOK THE JOB ON MOUNT HAKOBE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND IT'S NOT THAT FAR FROM HERE,
SO WHY WON'T SOMEBODY
GO LOOK FOR HIM?
- LISTEN, KID,
YOUR OLD MAN'S A WIZARD.
AND LIKE EVERY OTHER
WIZARD IN THIS GUILD,
HE CAN TAKE CARE
OF HIMSELF.
NOW GO HOME,
HAVE SOME MILK AND COOKIES,
AND WAIT!
- JERK!
- ( crashing )
- I HATE YOU ALL!
- THAT'S GOTTA BE TOUGH.
- I KNOW IT SOUNDS LIKE
THE MASTER DOESN'T CARE,
BUT HE REALLY IS WORRIED.
- ( crashing )
- Nab: WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
YOU ALMOST BROKE
THE BOARD, NATSU.
- ( sighs )
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD,
MASTER.
YOU KNOW HOW HE CAN BE.
I BET HE'S GOING UP
TO MOUNT HAKOBE TO SAVE MACAO.
- WHEN IS THAT KID
EVER GONNA GROW UP?
- WHO KNOWS?
GOING AFTER MACAO
ISN'T GONNA DO ANYTHING
EXCEPT HURT HIS PRIDE.
- REMEMBER NAB,
WE CAN'T CHOOSE
ANOTHER'S PATH.
JUST LEAVE HIM BE.
- WHY DID NATSU
GET SO UPSET?
- PROBABLY BECAUSE HE AND
ROMEO HAVE A LOT IN COMMON.
I THINK HE SEES
HIMSELF IN ROMEO.
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE
MEMBERS OF FAIRY TAIL,
IT DOESN'T MEAN WE HAVE
OUR OWN PERSONAL ISSUES.
WE'VE ALL HAD OUR FAIR SHARE
OF SUFFERING AND LOSS.
- ( horse neighs )
- Natsu: ( groans )
WHY'D YOU COME WITH US?
- Lucy:
I THOUGHT MAYBE I COULD HELP.
WOW, YOU REALLY DO HAVE
A SERIOUS CASE
OF MOTION SICKNESS,
DON'T YOU?
IT'S JUST ANOTHER REASON
TO FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
- Natsu:
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?!
- Lucy: OH, NOTHING.
FORGET I SAID ANYTHING.
- Mirajane: MANY YEARS AGO,
NATSU'S FATHER LEFT
AND NEVER CAME BACK.
- ( gasps )
- WELL, TECHNICALLY
IT WASN'T HIS REAL FATHER,
BUT THE ONE WHO RAISED HIM.
HE WAS ACTUALLY A DRAGON.
- ( roars )
- ( gasps )
HE WAS A WHAT?!
NATSU WAS REALLY
RAISED BY A DRAGON?
- Mirajane:
WHEN HE WAS A LITTLE BOY,
A DRAGON FOUND HIM
WANDERING THE FOREST.
HE TOOK HIM IN AND TAUGHT HIM
ALL ABOUT LANGUAGE,
CULTURE, AND MAGIC.
BUT ONE DAY,
THE DRAGON DISAPPEARED
AND NEVER RETURNED.
- Lucy: SO THAT DRAGON
MUST HAVE BEEN IGNEEL.
- Mirajane: THAT'S RIGHT.
AND NATSU LIVES FOR THE DAY
WHEN HE'LL FINALLY
SEE IGNEEL AGAIN.
IT'S KIND OF CUTE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- I GUESS WE'RE THERE.
- ALL RIGHT!
WE'VE STOPPED MOVING!
- Driver: I'M SORRY, BUT THIS
IS AS FAR AS I CAN G ET YOU.
- WHOA!
- WHERE THE HECK ARE WE, NATSU?
IT'S A FROZEN WASTELAND!
- WHY IS IT SO COLD?
I KNOW WE'RE ON A MOUNTAIN,
BUT IT'S SUMMER RIGHT NOW.
THERE SHOULDN'T BE A BLIZZARD
LIKE THIS ANYWHERE!
- THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR WEARING LIGHT CLOTHING.
- OH, PLEASE!
YOU'RE NOT DRESSED FOR IT.
NOW HAND OVER THAT BLANKET!
- GOSH, SHE JUST
KEEPS ON TALKING, HUH?
- AYE.
- OH, I KNOW.
OPEN GATE OF THE CLOCK
CONSTELLATION!
HOROLOGIUM!
- TICK, TOCK.
- A CLOCK, WHOA.
- THAT IS SO COOL.
- WAIT, I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
- SHE SAYS
"I'M STAYING IN HERE,
AND I'M NOT COMING OUT."
- THEN WHY'D YOU TAG ALONG?
- "WHAT KIND OF CRAZY JOB
WOULD FORCE MACAO
TO COME TO A PLACE LIKE THIS?"
SHE INQUIRES.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE ASKED THAT
BEFORE YOU CAME WITH US.
HE WENT TO SLAY A VULCAN.
IT'S A BIG MONSTER.
- ( gasps )
- "I WANT TO GO BACK
TO THE GUILD,"
SHE PROCLAIMS.
- GO AHEAD AND BE MY GUEST,
I SAY BACK.
- AYE.
- MACAO!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- ( chuckles )
- THAT'S A BIG VULCAN!
- HUH?
( snorts )
( chuckles )
- HEY, WAIT!
- ( knocking )
- ( gasps )
- ME LIKE HUMAN WOMAN.
- SO IT CAN TALK, HUH?
- "DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
HURRY UP AND SAVE ME,"
SHE YELLS FURIOUSLY.
- ( giggles )
- Narrator: NEAR THE SUMMIT
OF MOUNT HAKOBE...
- ( Vulcan grunting )
- "HOW DID I GET MYSELF
INTO THIS MESS.
AND WHAT'S WITH
THIS GIANT MONKEY?
WHY IS HE SO EXCITED?"
SHE ASKS TEARFULLY.
- WOMAN.
- ( whimpers )
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
WHERE'D YOU GO, HOROLOGIUM?
DON'T YOU DISAPPEAR ON ME!
- Horologium: SORRY,
BUT MY TIME IS UP.
TAKE CARE.
- GIVE ME AN EXTENSION, PLEASE!
- ( laughs )
- ( screams )
- HEY, YOU BIG APE!
WHERE'S MACAO?!
TELL ME!
WHOA!
( grunts )
- HMM?
- OHH...
WHOA.
THAT WASN'T COOL.
WHY DOES HE FEEL LIKE HE HAS TO
MAKE AN ENTRANCE ALL THE TIME?
- SPILL IT, MONKEY.
WHERE IS MY FRIEND?
- HUH?
- ( grunts )
YOU UNDERSTAND ME, RIGHT?
HE'S A HUMAN MAN.
NOW TELL ME WHERE HE IS.
- MAN?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WHERE ARE YOU HIDING HIM?
- DON'T YOU THINK YOU MIGHT
BE JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS?
- MAN! - HEY, I THINK
HE'S GONNA SHOW ME.
MACAO!
( grunts )
MONKEY!
- NATSU! - NO LIKE MAN.
ME LIKE WOMAN!
( whooping )
- THIS IS BAD NEWS.
HE CAN'T SURVIVE OUT THERE.
NATSU!
- WOMAN.
WOMAN WOMAN WOMAN
WOMAN WOMAN.
( chuckles )
- ALL RIGHT, YOU PERVY MONKEY,
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
OPEN, GATE OF THE GOLDEN BULL!
TAURUS!
- ( growls )
- COW?
- I SHOULD WARN YOU, MONKEY BOY,
TAURUS IS THE MOST POWERFUL
CELESTIAL SPIRIT
THAT I HAVE A CONTRACT WITH.
- OH, WOW, MISS LUCY.
I ALMOST FORGOT WHAT
A NICE FIGURE YOU HAVE.
WHY DON'T YOU COME
GIVE ME A SMOOCH?
- OH YEAH, AND HE'S
A BIG PERV TOO.
- NO TOUCH MY WOMAN!
- YOUR WOMAN?
THEM'S FIGHTING WORDS,
YOU MOO-NKEY!
- GET HIM!
- ( shouts )
- HE'S FAST.
- ( grunts )
- AAH!
- NATSU!
LOOKS LIKE THIS IS
THE END FOR ME.
- EPIC FAIL.
- HEY.
SO HOW COME THERE ARE MORE
MONSTERS NOW THAN WHEN I LEFT?
- HE'S A FRIEND, DUMMY!
ONE OF MY SPIRITS!
- THAT GUY?
- NOT HIM!  THE BULL.
WAIT A MINUTE, HOW WERE YOU
ABLE TO SURVIVE OUT THERE?
- ( chuckles )
HAPPY CAME TO SAVE ME.
THANKS, LITTLE BUDDY.
- AYE!
- SO YOU CAN'T HANDLE
OTHER MODES OF TRANSPORTATION,
BUT FLYING WITH HAPPY'S OKAY?
- WHAT KIND OF STUPID
QUESTION IS THAT?
HAPPY ISN'T A MODE
OF TRANSPORTATION.
HE'S MY FRIEND.
I MEAN, DUH.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT WAS TOTALLY WRONG OF ME
TO COMPARE THE TWO.
- ( sighs )
MY WOMAN!
( growls )
- YOU LISTEN UP.
I CONSIDER EVERYONE IN
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD MY FRIEND.
- ( grunts )
- WHETHER IT'S GRAMPS AND MIRA,
OR EVEN THOSE ANNOYING JERKS
GRAY AND ELFMAN.
- ( gasps )
- HAPPY AND LUCY TOO.
THEY'RE ALL MY FRIENDS.
WHICH IS WHY...
- ( shouts )
- ...I'M NOT LEAVING
WITHOUT MACAO!
- ( growls )
- AAH! - YOUR ICE ATTACK
HAS NO EFFECT ON FIRE.
- ( chuckles )
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
- HE GOT TAURUS'S AXE.
- PLEASE, BE CAREFUL,
MISS LUCY.
- ( grunts )
- AAH!
( grunts )
- NO!
- ( growls )
- GO BACK, TAURUS.
IF YOU GO BACK
BEYOND THE GATE,
YOUR AXE WILL DISAPPEAR TOO.
- ( straining )
- HUH?
- IS HE MELTING THE BLADE
WITH JUST HIS BODY HEAT?
- UH-HUH.
- OH YEAH, NOW I GOT
SOME FIRE IN MY BELLY.
- ( whimpers )
AAH!
- EAT THIS!
FIRE DRAGON IRON FIST!
- ( moans )
- WE BEAT HIM!
- YEAH, BUT WASN'T THIS MONKEY
SUPPOSED TO TELL US
WHERE YOUR FRIEND IS?
- OH. ( chuckles )
FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
- WELL, I DON'T THINK
HE'S GONNA DO MUCH TALKING.
( yelps )
- WHAT IN THE HECK
WAS THAT?
( gasps )
MACAO?
- ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT BIG PERVERTED MONKEY
WAS ACTUALLY YOUR FRIEND
THIS WHOLE TIME?!
- YEAH, HE MUST HAVE BEEN
TAKEN OVER BY THAT VULCAN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"TAKEN OVER"?
- IT MUST HAVE USED
A POSSESSION SPELL ON HIM.
YOU SEE, VULCANS SURVIVE
BY STEALING PEOPLE'S BODIES
AND TAKING THEM OVER.
THEY'RE EVIL BODY SNATCHERS.
- ( laughs )
- IT LOOKS LIKE
HE PUT UP A GOOD FIGHT
BEFORE THAT VULCAN
FINALLY GOT TO HIM THOUGH.
- MACAO,
DON'T YOU DIE ON ME.
ROMEO'S WAITING FOR YOU.
OPEN YOUR EYES!
- ( sighs )
NATSU?
- YOU'RE OKAY.
- ( chuckles )
- I'M SO PATHETIC.
I DEFEATED 19 OF THOSE BRUTES.
- HUH?
- BUT THE 20TH,
THAT'S THE ONE THAT GOT ME.
I'M SO ANGRY WITH MYSELF.
I'M EMBARRASSED
TO GO HOME AND FACE ROMEO.
- DON'T BE LIKE THAT.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU BEAT 19 MONSTERS.
- NO WAY.  THERE WERE 20 OF
THOSE GIANT MONKEY THINGS?
AND HE TOOK ON THE JOB
ALL BY HIMSELF?
- NOW LET'S GO HOME.
YOUR LITTLE BOY'S
BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
- ( chuckles )
- THEY'RE AMAZING.
I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO COMPARE TO THEM.
- WHY ARE YOU GRINNING
LIKE THAT, LUCY?
IT'S CREEPY.
- I'LL SHOW YOU CREEPY.
WATCH YOUR BACK.
- FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS
ARE A JOKE, ROMEO.
- YEAH, EVERYBODY KNOWS THEY'RE
JUST A BUNCH OF DRUNKEN COWARDS.
- I'M GONNA BE A KNIGHT
WHEN I GROW UP.
NOT SOME DUMB WIZARD.
- YEAH, THEY'RE DIRTY
AND THEY SMELL LIKE BOOZE.
- PLEASE, DAD.
GO TO THE BOARD
AND TAKE A JOB.
I CAN'T HANDLE ALL
THIS TEASING ANYMORE.
- ( chuckles )
SURE.
- ( sniffles )
- HEY, ROMEO!
( laughs )
- ( gasps )
- ( all chuckle )
- DAD!
- ( gasps )
- YOU CAME BACK.
I'M SO SORRY, DAD.
- NO, I'M SORRY FOR
MAKING YOU WORRY.
- I CAN HANDLE IT,
'CAUSE I'M A WIZARD'S SON.
- NEXT TIME THOSE BULLIES
PICK ON YOU,
HERE'S WHAT I
WANT YOU TO SAY.
"CAN YOUR OLD MAN DEFEAT
19 MONSTERS ALL BY HIMSELF?
'CAUSE MINE CAN."
- ( giggles )
NATSU!
HAPPY!
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP!
- NO PROB, KIDDO.
- AYE.
- LUCY, THANKS FOR HELPING
TO BRING MY DADDY
BACK TO ME!
- ( laughs )
Lucy: JULY FOURTH,
IT WAS A SUNNY DAY
FOLLOWED BY A BLIZZARD,
BUT IT ENDED UP
SUNNY AGAIN.
I'LL ADMIT THE PEOPLE
IN FAIRY TAIL ARE CRAZY,
BUT THEY'RE ALSO
WARMHEARTED, NICE,
AND A LOT OF FUN
TO BE AROUND.
I KNOW I'M STILL
A NEWCOMER AROUND HERE,
BUT I CAN'T HELP IT.
I ALREADY LOVE THIS GUILD!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I FINALLY GET TO PICK MY FIRST
JOB ON THE REQUEST BOARD.
OH, GOSH.
I'M SO NERVOUS.
I HOPE I CAN HANDLE IT.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY, LUCY.
- OH, HEY, MIRA.
- I HEARD ALL ABOUT
YOUR EXPLOITS THE OTHER DAY.
HAPPY SAID YOU BEAT UP
SOME GORILLA MERCENARIES.
- ACTUALLY, IT WAS NATSU.
AND THAT'S NOT QUITE
WHAT HAPPENED.
- Mirajane: SO WHAT
DID YOU DECIDE TO TAKE ON
AS YOUR FIRST JOB, LUCY?
- Lucy: MAID WORK.
- Mirajane: EW... REALLY?