- Natsu: PREVIOUSLY,
ON FAIRY TAIL!
- Happy: THE GUILD'S REALLY
GROWN THIS PAST YEAR!
WE'VE GOT A BUNCH
OF NEW MEMBERS.
- Natsu: YEAH, LUCY CAME ALONG,
THEN GAJEEL AND JUVIA.
- Lucy: AND DON'T FORGET WENDY
AND CARLA JUST JOINED, TOO!
I GUESS I MUST BE SOME KINDA
LUCKY CHARM FOR FAIRY TAIL.
- Happy: OOH, LIKE ONE
OF THOSE LUCKY CATS?
- Natsu: OR A JINX!
- Lucy: WATCH IT, PYRO!
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- HMMM, NONE OF THEM ARE
PARTICULARLY ENTICING, ARE THEY?
- Mirajane: OH MY,
YOU'RE BACK AND ALREADY
LOOKING FOR YOUR NEXT JOB!
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
GETTING THE HANG
OF THE WORK WE DO AROUND
HERE PRETTY QUICKLY.
- SO FAR SHE'S ONLY
TAKEN THE SMALL,
LOW-PAYING JOBS
AROUND THE CITY,
SO SHE COULD STAND TO
BE A BIT MORE AMBITIOUS.
- I'M TRYING!
- Mirajane: THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH TAKING SMALL STEPS
TO BUILD EXPERIENCE.
IT'S PERFECTLY NORMAL
TO START THAT WAY.
- SHE'S RIGHT, BUT DON'T YOU
WANNA START GETTING INTO
SOME OF THE BIG-TIME
JOBS LIKE WE DO?
- THEY'RE FUN, AND YOU CAN
VISIT SOME COOL NEW PLACES.
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
THE SOONER I'M ABLE TO TAKE
ON SOME OF THE BIGGER JOBS,
THE SOONER I CAN BE MORE
HELPFUL TO THE GUILD!
- Happy: WENDY'S FIRST BIG JOB?
- SHE JUST WANTS TO DO
HER PART AROUND HERE, HUH?
- GOOD ON YOU, WENDY!
- NOW THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
YOUNG, IDEALISTIC, AND FULL OF
HEART! I'LL DRINK TO THAT!
- THANKS A LOT, YOU GUYS!
- LUCY SURE COULD TAKE A PAGE
OR TWO FROM HER BOOK, EH?
- ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY I'M NOT
HELPFUL OR I'VE GOT NO HEART?
- WOW, TOUGH QUESTION.
- NO, IT'S NOT, STUPID CAT!
- I'M HELPFUL BY
INSPIRING OTHERS
WITH MY INNER AND OUTER BEAUTY!
- YOU HELP ME LAUGH,
BY SAYING STUFF LIKE THAT!
- YOU'RE SO RUDE! OH, YOU WANNA
LAUGH AT ME, DO YA? COME HERE!
- ANYWAY, I'M SURE EVERYONE
WHO'S BEEN OUT
ON JOBS FOR A WHILE
WILL BE SURPRISED
WHEN THEY GET BACK.
YOU MIGHT BE THE YOUNGEST
NEW RECRUIT WE'VE HAD.
- OH, YEAH, WHAT
WILL GILDARTS SAY?
- I HAVEN'T HEARD
THAT NAME IN AGES.
- AND NOBODY'S HEARD FROM
HIM IN A LONG TIME, EITHER.
HE'S BEEN ON THAT SAME
JOB FOR HOW MANY YEARS NOW?
- I DON'T KNOW,
LIKE THREE, MAYBE?
- I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
DON'T FORGET WHO
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I MEAN, IT'S GILDARTS
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
- HE'S FINE,
THAT GUY CAN HANDLE ANYTHING.
- IT JUST SO HAPPENS,
WE HAVE A JOB REQUEST
THAT'S PERFECT FOR YOU.
THIS POOR PERSON IS IN
DIRE NEED OF A WIZARD
WHO CAN SOOTHE HIS HEART.
IT DOESN'T PAY A LOT, BUT
IT DOES INVOLVE SOME TRAVEL,
WHICH WOULD BE GOOD EXPERIENCE.
- WHERE IS IT ANYWAY?
ALL THE WAY OVER IN ONIBAS?
- WHAT ARE THEY ASKING FOR?
- UH, WELL, IT SAYS
"THANK YOU VERY MUCH."
- THANKS FOR NO REASON?
- HEY! I KNOW THAT!
THAT'S RINGING A
WEIRD BELL INSIDE ME!
IT'S HOPELESS. I'M DOOMED.
WHY? BECAUSE AGAIN AND AGAIN,
I'M LEFT OUT IN THE COLD.
MY ACTORS DESERT ME,
AND MY ART IS KEPT
HIDDEN FROM THE WORLD.
THE TOLL ON MY
PSYCHE IS ENORMOUS.
THANK YOU VERY
MUCH, SIGNED LAVIAN.
- THAT NAME SOUNDS
REALLY FAMILIAR.
- HE'S THAT CRAZY LITTLE
GUY THAT RUNS THE THEATRE.
- REMEMBER THAT HORRIBLE TRAIN
WRECK OF A PLAY WE WERE ALL IN?
- WHOA! YOU MEAN
"FREDRICK AND YANDERICA!"
- Gray: WENDY, PLEASE, TAKE MY
ADVICE AND DON'T DO IT.
- Natsu: YEAH, HE'S A TOTAL
SLAVE DRIVER, FOR REAL.
- Lucy: THE WORK WAS HARD,
THE PLAY WAS TERRIBLE.
AND HE MADE US DO LIKE FIFTY
SHOWS BEFORE WE COULD LEAVE.
- Carla: I'M AGAINST IT AS WELL.
JUST BECAUSE THE
JOB IS AVAILABLE,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO TAKE IT.
SOMETHING FEELS WRONG ABOUT IT.
- YOU'RE NORMALLY RIGHT
ABOUT THESE KINDS OF THINGS.
BUT, THIS GUY SOUNDS LIKE
HE REALLY NEEDS SOME HELP.
- FOLLOW YOUR HEART,
BUT USE YOUR HEAD, CHILD.
BESIDES, IF I MAY
SPEAK CANDIDLY,
A JOB SUCH AS THIS, I DON'T
THINK YOU'RE QUITE READY YET.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE!
I AM READY TO DO THIS.
YOU'LL SEE!
- NO, I'M AFRAID THAT
I WON'T SEE, CHILD.
BECAUSE I WILL NOT
BE GOING WITH YOU.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY THE HECK ARE YOU
TWO FIGHTING ABOUT THIS?
YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE
TO BE SO HARD ON HER
ALL THE TIME, YOU KNOW?
- ( scoffs )
- ( laughing sheepishly )
WELL, FINE! 'CAUSE I'M
GONNA TAKE THIS JOB ANYWAY!
- OH, MY, WAIT.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF
GOING ALONE, ARE YOU?
- YEP! IT'LL BE EVEN
MORE OF AN EXPERIENCE!
- Makarov: HOLD YOUR HORSES,
YOUNG LADY!
I KNOW YOU HAVE A GREAT
DEAL OF GOOD INTENTIONS,
BUT IT'S SIMPLY NOT
WISE TO GO ALONE.
AND SPEAKING AS THE
MASTER OF THIS GUILD,
I ABSOLUTELY FORBID IT.
( gulping )
( exhales )
WHICH OF YOU HAS
BEEN THERE BEFORE?
LET ME SEE. HAPPY!
- WHO ME?
- UM-HMM.
AND, YOU AS WELL, FRIED.
GO WITH THEM, YOU SEEM
TO BE IDLE AT THE MOMENT.
- IF THAT IS YOUR WISH,
MASTER, I SHALL.
- WHAT?
- All: THAT TEAM
IS SUPER RANDOM!
- Wendy: WELL, I GUESS
WE'RE ON OUR WAY!
- ( scoffs )
- TRY TO BE CAREFUL
OUT THERE, YOU GUYS.
- HEY, FRIED.
YOU BETTER NOT LET ANYTHING
HAPPEN TO OUR GIRL, YOU HEAR ME?
- I SWEAR ON MY HONOR,
I WILL KEEP HER SAFE.
- REMEMBER THAT THIS IS A
LEARNING EXPERIENCE FOR WENDY.
SO PLEASE KEEP YOUR
INVOLVEMENT TO A MINIMUM.
- WHY US THREE?
- ( scoffs )
- SHOULD WE REALLY
LET HER GO LIKE THIS?
- I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING FOR US TO WORRY ABOUT
AS LONG AS FRIED
STAYS BY HER SIDE.
- BUT HE'S SO WEIRD AND RIGID.
NOT TO MENTION ALOOF.
SERIOUSLY, I CAN'T
READ THAT GUY AT ALL.
- Man: DUE TO
A WRECK ON THE TRACKS,
THE TRAIN BOUND FOR ONIBAS
STATION IS OUT OF SERVICE!
I REPEAT.
THE TRAIN BOUND FOR ONIBAS
STATION IS OUT OF SERVICE!
- OUR FIRST CHALLENGE APPEARS.
HOW SHALL WE PROCEED, WENDY?
- WELL, DON'T FORGET
I CAN USE AERA MAGIC.
I'M PRETTY SURE I COULD
FLY YOU ALL THE WAY THERE,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANNA DO.
- MM-MM.
THAT'S NICE OF YOU TO OFFER,
BUT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO AS MUCH
OF THIS JOB AS I CAN ON MY OWN.
SO THAT MEANS I'M JUST GONNA
HAVE TO WALK
ALL THE WAY TO ONIBAS.
- HUH?
BUT IT'LL TAKE US FOREVER
TO GET THERE ON FOOT!
TALK SOME SENSE INTO HER, FRIED!
- I AGREE, THE MATTER
IS SETTLED, THEN.
- YA SEE? EVEN
FRIED THINKS IT'S CRAZY.
- I, TOO, SHALL WALK.
- ( exclaims )
- IT IS YOUR WISH.
MY PRIMARY DUTY
IS TO SUPPORT YOU.
AND AFTER ALL, IT'S THE
ONE RULE MASTER GAVE ME,
THEREFORE, I MUST FOLLOW IT.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR LISTENING TO ME!
- I WISH HE WOULD'VE
LISTENED TO ME.
SO WE'RE SERIOUSLY GONNA
WALK ALL THE WAY THERE?
- WELL, TO BE
COMPLETELY ACCURATE.
WENDY AND I WILL
BE WALKING THERE.
WHILE YOU, NO DOUBT, WILL FLY.
- WHAT IN THE HECK KIND OF
DIFFERENCE DOES THAT MAKE?
- ACCURACY CAN MAKE A
WORLD OF DIFFERENCE.
AS ONE WHO USES ENCHANTMENTS,
I MUST ALWAYS BE
PRECISE IN MY WORDS.
- Happy: EITHER WAY,
IT'S GONNA TAKE FOREVER.
- Wendy: THEN LET'S GO.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO GET
THERE BEFORE SUNSET.
- WHAT'S THIS? WENDY TOOK
THE JOB AT THE THEATRE?
- AFRAID SO.
AND I WAS MORE THAN WILLING
TO GO ALONG TO HELP HER,
BUT MASTER THOUGHT
THAT HAPPY AND...
- AH-A-EE-EWE-A-OOH-AH-OH-KAH...
- KAY-KEE-KU-KAY-KU-KAH-KU...
- SO WHY EXACTLY
ARE YOU DOING THAT?
- ALL THINGS ARE READY,
IF OUR MIND BE SO.
- BE READY FOR WHAT?
- MASTER WAS RIGHT,
BUT I STILL CAN'T STOP WORRYING
ABOUT SUCH A SMALL GROUP
BEING UP TO THE TASK AT HAND.
THEREFORE, I'M GOING TO HELP.
- ARE YOU ALREADY PACKED?
AND IS IT JUST ME OR
ARE YOU CARRYING
MORE LUGGAGE THAN NORMAL?
- WELL, THIS IS A SPECIAL JOB.
- UH, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD THAT.
- I TOOK IT IN LIEU
OF MONETARY PAYMENT,
A CHOICE I'VE NEVER
ONCE REGRETTED.
THE MERE SIGHT OF THESE
PROPS AND COSTUMES,
NEVER FAILS TO LIFT MY SPIRITS.
SOMETIMES, I EVEN AMUSE
MYSELF BY RECREATING THE PLAY
AS A ONE WOMAN SHOW.
- I DIDN'T REALIZE IT
WAS THAT SPECIAL TO YOU.
OR, APPARENTLY,
THAT YOU HAD GONE
COMPLETELY OUT OF YOUR MIND.
- BAD NEWS!
THE TRAINS AREN'T RUNNING
TO ONIBAS STATION TODAY!
- HUH?
- THEN WE SHOULD
TRAVEL THERE IMMEDIATELY
TO SEE THAT WENDY AND
THE OTHERS MADE IT.
WELL, LUCY?
- YEAH, OKAY.
ARE YOU COMING WITH US?
- WHY MUST YOU INSIST
ON MEDDLING?
SHE CHOSE TO GO
IN SPITE OF MY ADVICE.
AND BESIDES THAT,
YOU DON'T CHOOSE
A JOB SIMPLY BECAUSE
IT'S FAR AWAY AND INCONVENIENT.
YOU CHOOSE A JOB THAT BOTH
PAYS WELL AND HONES YOUR SKILLS.
I'M SURE THAT THIS
ONE DOES NEITHER.
IT'S A COMPLETE WASTE
OF HER TIME AND ENERGY.
AND ALL OF OURS AS WELL.
- SO, WHY DID YOU CHOOSE
TO COME ALONG WITH US?
- I KNOW THE WAY SHE THINKS.
SHE'LL STUBBORNLY REFUSE
ANY ALTERNATE MEANS OF
TRANSPORTATION
AND INSIST ON WALKING THERE.
- IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG TRIP.
- Lucy: YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
IT ALREADY FEELS LIKE AN
ETERNITY WITH THESE TWO.
- Wendy: I'M SORRY IF I'M MAKING
THIS JOB MORE DIFFICULT FOR YOU.
- Fried: YOU'RE MY COMRADE.
NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
- Happy: COME ON,
CAN WE PLEASE TAKE A BREAK?
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW
IF THAT'S SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
I CAN SENSE THAT THERE'S A
THUNDERSTORM COMING PRETTY SOON.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
THIS WEATHER IS GORGEOUS!
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( rain pattering )
- Happy: THIS
WEATHER'S HORRIBLE!
- Wendy: WE NEED TO HURRY
AND GET OUT OF THE RAIN!
- Fried: ( thinking ) I COULD
EASILY CREATE AN ENCHANTMENT
TO SHIELD US FROM THE ELEMENTS.
IT WOULD TAKE A TINY FRACTION
OF MY MAGICAL POWER TO DO SO.
HOWEVER, THE RULE IS TO AVOID
ASSISTING WENDY
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
BUT I AM TASKED WITH
KEEPING HER SAFE.
IF SHE WERE TO CATCH COLD,
I WOULD BE TO BLAME.
SHOULD I TAKE ACTION,
OR LEAVE HER BE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
I NEED YOUR GUIDANCE, LAXUS!
FOR YEARS IN THE THUNDER
LEGION I FOLLOWED YOUR LEAD.
HOW WOULD YOU DEAL WITH THIS?
I NEED TO KNOW THE RULES!
LAXUS!
- MR. FRIED!
I FOUND A CAVE!
- OH.
MUCH BETTER.
IT SEEMS INACTION PROVED
TO BE THE CORRECT CHOICE.
- Happy: UM, WHAT ARE YOU
MUMBLING ABOUT?
- ( chuckles )
YOU NEEDN'T CONCERN
YOURSELF WITH IT, CAT.
- YEP, YOU SERIOUSLY
GOTTA WONDER
WHAT'S GOING ON IN
THAT GUY'S HEAD SOMETIMES.
- "IS IT ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY
THAT WE SQUEEZE OURSELVES
INTO SUCH A TINY SPACE?"
THE CAT INQUIRES UNCOMFORTABLY.
"YES, OF COURSE IT IS. BUT, IF
YOU'D RATHER GET DRENCHED,
BE MY GUEST."
THE YOUNG GIRL
REPLIES QUITE TESTILY.
"OHHH, I HOPE THAT ALL MY PROPS
AND COSTUMES DON'T GET WET."
THE LADY GROANS WORRIEDLY.
- Natsu: SAY WHAT? LUCY AND THEM
WENT ON THE JOB TOO?
- OUI. THEY DID.
- I GUESS THEY COULDN'T
STAND NOT BEING INVOLVED.
- HOW DID YOU MISS ALL THAT?
WHAT IN THE HECK
HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?
- I WAS SLEEPING.
ALL RIGHT, IF THEY'RE ALL GOING,
I DON'T SEE WHY I HAVE TO
SIT AROUND HERE ALL DAY!
- All: NATSU!
- DO YOU THINK THAT HE
KNOWS ABOUT THE TRAIN?
HE WON'T BE HAPPY.
- ( yells )
I DON'T WANT TO RIDE THIS THING!
BUT I GOTTA DO IT!
I GOTTA GET TO ONIBAS SOON!
BUT I HATE THE TRAIN SO MUCH.
- WE CAN'T WAIT HERE ALL DAY FOR
YOU TO MAKE UP YOUR MIND, KID.
WE'RE LATE ENOUGH AS IT IS!
- OKAY! I'LL DO IT.
JUST TRY TO KEEP IT
FROM SHAKING SO BAD.
- YOU WANT ME TO DO WHAT?
- Female Announcer:
ATTENTION, PASSENGERS.
DUE TO A WRECK ON THE TRACKS,
THIS TRAIN WILL MAKE ITS FINAL
STOP JUST BEFORE ONIBAS STATION
AND THEN RETURN TO MAGNOLIA.
I REPEAT.
THIS TRAIN WILL NOT BE REACHING
THE ONIBAS STATION TODAY.
WE DEEPLY REGRET
THIS INCONVENIENCE
AND APPRECIATE YOUR
COOPERATION AND UNDERSTANDING.
- Happy: AT LEAST IT FINALLY
STOPPED RAINING.
- Wendy: BUT IT'LL BE
GETTING DARK SOON.
I'M AFRAID THAT WE MIGHT
HAVE TO SLEEP OUTSIDE TONIGHT.
- THAT CAVE WILL SERVE
AS A SUFFICIENT PLACE
TO REST FOR THE EVENING.
THOUGH THERE IS THE
ISSUE OF PROVISIONS.
- IT'S NOT CHEATING TO HELP
US FIND FOOD, YOU KNOW.
EVEN MASTER WOULD SAY IT'S
A HEALTH AND SAFETY ISSUE.
- YES, OF COURSE.
I AM FULLY COGNIZANT OF
WHAT MY OBLIGATIONS ON THIS
PARTICULAR MISSION MAY OR
MAY NOT REQUIRE ME TO DO.
- COULD YOU USE ANY MORE
WORDS IN THAT SENTENCE?
- I'VE ALREADY DETERMINED
THE BEST SOURCE OF NUTRITION.
IN FACT, I'VE TAKEN
STEPS TO PROCURE IT.
- WOW, REALLY?
- THIS GUY MAY BE SUPER WEIRD,
BUT I GUESS THERE WAS A GOOD
REASON MASTER SENT HIM WITH US.
- WITHIN THE BOUNDS
OF THIS ENCHANTMENT,
WINGFISH SHALL
FALL FROM THE SKY!
- WHY IS IT GOTTA BE WINGFISH?
- Fried: THEIR ANNUAL
MIGRATORY PATH
FLOWS DIRECTLY OVER THIS REGION.
THEY COME HERE IN FLOCKS
AT THIS TIME EVERY YEAR
TO FIND A MATE AND SPAWN.
- ARE THESE REALLY EVEN EDIBLE?
- MM-MM.
I WOULDN'T SAY THAT
THEY'RE "EDIBLE."
I CAUGHT SOME ONCE
AND IT WAS THE GROSSEST THING
I'VE EVER TASTED IN MY LIFE.
- NO DOUBT AN ASSERTION
MADE BY AN AMATEUR.
THE FLAW LIES NOT WITH THE
FISH, BUT THE PREPARATION.
BRINGING OUT THEIR NATURAL
FLAVOR, TAKES SKILL.
( grunts )
- OH, WHAT A NICE SURPRISE.
I HAD NO IDEA YOU'RE
GOOD AT COOKING!
I'M NOT ONE TO BOAST,
BUT MY COMRADES IN
THE THUNDER LEGION
ENJOYED MY OCCASIONAL DISHES.
AND YOU MIGHT, TOO.
- THAT LOOKS SO GOOD!
- PRESENTATION IS
VERY IMPORTANT.
NOW, I HOPE YOU ENJOY
THE FLAVOR AS WELL.
- THANKS FOR THE FOOD!
- THAT'S IT, TASTED EXACTLY
THE SAME WHEN I MADE IT.
- I THINK I SAW SOME NUTS
AND BERRIES OVER THERE.
- LET'S PICK SOME OF THOSE.
- AYE.
- HM, NUTRITION MUST
ALWAYS TRUMP FLAVOR.
WE WIZARDS MUST KEEP
OUR STRENGTH AT ANY COST.
- AND WE'RE SURE THAT THIS
IS OUR ONLY CHOICE FOR FOOD?
- WHY ELSE DO YOU THINK
WE'RE EATING THIS?
- Carla: A PERFECT EXAMPLE
OF WHY I DIDN'T WANT TO COME
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
- Female Announcer: ATTENTION.
THE ONIBAS-MAGNOLIA
TRAIN IS NOW ARRIVING
AND WILL BE DEPARTING FOR
THE RETURN JOURNEY SOON.
WE APPRECIATE
YOUR UNDERSTANDING,
AND HOPE YOUR JOURNEY
IS SAFE AND COMFORTABLE.
- SIR! PLEASE, YOU
HAVE TO GET UP!
WE'RE DEPARTING AGAIN!
YOU'VE BEEN RIDING THIS TRAIN
BACK AND FORTH SINCE YESTERDAY!
YOU CAN'T STAY ON FOREVER!
- ( groaning )
- Happy: GREAT, OUT OF THE
MOUNTAINS AND INTO THE DESERT!
- Wendy: YOU DON'T SEEM TO BE
BOTHERED BY THE HEAT, MR. FRIED.
- HE'S PROBABLY USING SOME KIND
OF SPELL TO COOL HIMSELF DOWN.
- NO, I WOULD NEVER DENY
MY COMRADES COMFORT
TO CLAIM IT ALL FOR MY OWN.
IT'S SIMPLY MIND OVER MATTER.
- HOT. OH, SO HOT.
- HAPPY!
HOLD ON, YOU'LL FEEL
BETTER REAL SOON, OKAY?
- SHE KNOWS THAT SPELL
WILL DRAIN HER MAGIC ENERGY.
BUT SHE IS SO KINDHEARTED,
SHE DOESN'T HESITATE.
HER CONCERN FOR OTHERS IS MUCH
GREATER THAN THAT FOR HERSELF.
PLEASE, STOP!
YOU NEEDN'T DEPLETE YOUR POWER.
ALLOW ME TO ASSIST HIM.
- DO YOU KNOW HEALING MAGIC?
- FIRST, WE LAY HIM
PRONE ON THIS ROCK.
THEN, I INSCRIBE
THE ENCHANTMENT.
THOSE WITHIN THE BOUNDS
OF THIS ENCHANTMENT,
SHALL NOT BE AFFECTED BY HEAT!
- I REALLY HOPED I WAS NEVER
GONNA GET COOKED AGAIN.
- THE RESULTS OF AN
ENCHANTMENT SUCH AS THIS
ARE NOT ALWAYS IMMEDIATE.
- AND ONCE HE LEAVES IT, ISN'T
HE JUST GONNA GET
BURNED UP AGAIN?
- I'M FRIED.
- Lucy: WE'RE STILL GOING
THE RIGHT WAY, AREN'T WE?
- Carla: UNFORTUNATELY, THIS IS
HOW YOU GET THERE ON FOOT!
- STAY BACK!
- ERZA!
- Fried: WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
MUCH FARTHER TO GO.
DON'T LOSE HEART.
- Wendy: THERE'S A STORM COMING!
- OH, NO! YOU MEAN A SAND STORM?
- Fried: THIS DESERT IS KNOWN
FOR ITS "CURSED SANDSTORMS!"
- Happy: WHAT?
WE GOTTA FIND A PLACE TO HIDE!
- THERE IS NO PLACE TO
HIDE IN THIS TERRAIN.
RUN!
- I'M TRYING,
BUT I'M STILL SINKING.
- Carla: CAN'T YOU DO
SOMETHING TO HELP?
- Lucy: I KNOW!
- YOU WANT TO
PUNISH ME? PRINCESS?
- OH, COME ON!
I NEED YOU TO HELP ERZA!
- AS YOU WISH.
- ( rattling )
- PRINCESS, IT SEEMS SHE'S
TOO HEAVY FOR ME TO MOVE.
- I AM NOT!
- NO WAY, NOT EVEN A CELESTIAL
SPIRIT CAN GET HER OUT?
- Wendy: HEY, LUCY!
OH, AND CARLA, YOU CAME TOO?
- ( scoffs )
- Lucy: WE CAME BECAUSE WE
WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
DOING BETTER THAN WE ARE.
- Happy: ERZA! WHAT ARE YOU
DOING DOWN THERE?
- YEAH, ABOUT THAT.
- Fried: SHE'S STUCK.
PLUS, THAT CURSED SANDSTORM
CONTINUES TO BEAR DOWN ON US.
- HUH?
- ( roaring )
- ( Lucy screaming )
- SAVE YOURSELVES AND
GO ON WITHOUT ME!
- Lucy: DON'T GIVE UP, VIRGO!
- THIS WEIGHT IS
QUITE PERPLEXING.
IT'S NOT UNLIKE A GIANT
MASS OF ROCK OR IRON.
- WHAT IS IT?
MAYBE IT'S HER ARMOR
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT
SHE'S CARRYING AROUND WITH HER?
- I'M STILL HOLDING ON TO
THE PROPS AND COSTUMES.
- WHAT?
- ALL THAT STUFF
MUST WEIGH A TON!
- I KNOW, BUT THE SHOW
CAN'T GO ON WITHOUT THEM.
- WE'RE NOT EVEN SUPPOSED TO BE
PUTTING ON A PLAY THIS TIME!
- FAREWELL, DEAR FRIENDS.
I WILL ALWAYS TREASURE
OUR TIME TOGETHER.
THEY'RE GONE.
AND A PIECE OF MY
HEART GOES WITH THEM!
- BE GLAD YOU'RE ALIVE
TO DIG 'EM UP LATER!
- SHALL I PUNISH HER?
- ( roaring )
- Carla: IT'S TOO LATE!
THE STORM'S RIGHT OVER US!
- Fried: IF WE GET CAUGHT IN ITS
GRIP, WE WILL NEVER ESCAPE IT!
- ( Lucy whimpering )
- DON'T BE AFRAID!
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT!
- WENDY, NO!
- SKY DRAGON ROAR!
- ( roaring )
( groaning )
- Fried: SHE DID IT.
THE STORM'S DISAPPEARED.
- OH, YEAH!
- THAT WAS AWESOME! WOO-HOO!
- ( laughing sheepishly )
- HM.
- OH, THANK YOU!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
- HIS SPIRITS
DON'T SEEM CRUSHED.
- THE ACTORS AND MYSELF
HAVE ALL KISSED AND MADE UP!
THE PLAY HAS EVEN OPENED
TO A SOLD OUT AUDIENCE!
STANDING ROOM ONLY!
THANK YOU ALL SO VERY MUCH!
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
WE RISKED OUR LIVES
TRYING TO GET HERE
AND YOU DON'T NEED US?
- I WORKED LIKE A DOG
TO DIG THESE THINGS UP!
- THAT'S IT, I GIVE UP.
- ALL THOSE DREADFUL WINGFISH I
ATE ARE FINALLY GETTING TO ME.
I THINK I'M GOING TO BE SICK.
I AM!
I CAN'T STAND UP ANYMORE.
- Natsu: HEY!
- IT'S NATSU!
- THEY FINALLY FIXED
THE DANG TRACKS.
SO I'M HERE NOW.
UGH, I MUST HAVE RIDDEN THAT
STUPID, SHAKY, TRAIN
BACK AND FORTH A MILLION TIMES.
( groans )
- Lavian: MY WORD!
- HE'S NOT HAPPY ANYMORE!
- LOITERING IN FRONT OF MY
THEATRE IS BAD FOR BUSINESS!
YOU THERE!
- Wendy: YES, SIR?
- Lavian: PLEASE REMOVE THESE
VAGRANTS FROM MY PROPERTY.
I'M AWARE THAT THIS IS A VERY
BIG JOB, BUT I'LL PAY YOU.
- HUH?
( sighs )
MY FIRST BIG JOB IS
KICKING OUT MY FRIENDS.
- NO SHAME IN IT, CHILD.
THEY CAME HERE
WANTING TO HELP YOU,
AND NOW IN A ROUNDABOUT WAY,
YOU'RE SIMPLY
RETURNING THE FAVOR.
THIS IS QUITE A RESPECTABLE JOB,
SO YOU SHOULD CARRY
IT OUT WITH PRIDE.
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- WELL, I'M CONFIDENT IT IS.
- ( chuckles )
YOU'RE RIGHT!
( chuckles )
- AND THANK YOU ALL
VERY MUCH AS WELL.
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: ALRIGHT! I'M STOKED!
IT'S OFFICIALLY
ALMOST RACE TIME!
- Natsu: SWEET! I'M TAKING THAT
CHECKERED FLAG
THIS YEAR FOR SURE!
- Happy: ( laughs ) DID YOU
FORGET WHAT KIND OF MAGIC
I CAN DO? I CAN HOP, SKIP,
AND FLY MY WAY STRAIGHT
TO THE FINISH LINE!
- Natsu: KEEP DREAMING.
THE RULES SAY YOU GOTTA
DO THE WHOLE THING ON FOOT!
- Happy: WHAT? AW, MAN!
- Both: NEXT TIME,
24-HOUR ENDURANCE ROAD RACE
- Happy: THIS STINKS,
EVERYONE IN THE GUILD
RUNS FASTER THAN ME.
GUESS I'LL BE
SITTING THIS ONE OUT.
- Natsu: CARLA'S RUNNING!
- Happy: ME TOO!