♪
[NATSU] Previously,
on Fairy Tail!
[NATSU]
We're here.
Forgive me.
I've been such a fool.
I forgot the most
important thing of all.
I wasn't protecting
everyone around me.
[AZUMA]
Unbelieveable!
[ERZA] They were the ones
protecting me all along.
Now I repay the favor!
[AZUMA] Is this the
strength she was talking about?
The power to
protect those close to her.
It comes from
the bond they share.
What an amazing guild!
Well done.
[ERZA]
What's happening to you?
It's like you're being
swallowed by the ground.
[HAPPY]
Freezing Fighting Spirit!
[ERZA]
What's going on?
I suppose that I was
a bit too careless earlier.
Lost magic takes a heavy toll.
I'll honor my word.
Your friends' power
will be returned to them.
[ERZA]
Let me ask you.
Do you know a man named Jellal?
[AZUMA]
Yes.
Supposedly he lost his
mind after being possessed
by Zeref's spirit.
Or That's what he believed.
It left him
an empty shell,
living a life without meaning.
Was he close
to your heart as well?
My condolences.
That was also Ultear's doing.
It was all part
of an elaborate scheme that
spanned over the course
of several years.
Meant to distract the council
from our actions at the time.
Her skills
are truly terrifying.
Perhaps that's the reason why
Master Hades chooses to keep
her closest to his side.
Explain something to me.
Why does your guild
seek Zeref so intently?
To get closer
to the primordial magic.
Magic that has existed
since the world's creation.
That's why.
The Primordial magic.
And what would happen if
you were ever able to attain it?
Jellal had dreams.
He was dreaming of paradise.
Of heaven.
[ERZA]
Wait!!
Magic from
the world's creation.
Wait a sec.
I'm startin' to feel it again!
Did something
happen just now?
My magic
power's coming back.
Do you feel it?
Yeah.
It's back alright!
So that means.
Let's get to work!
Very good.
Back in business!
[BIXLOW]
Let's rock babies!
[TOMMENS]
Let's rock!
I wonder
what just happened.
Well, whatever it was,
our magic power is
back to normal now!
Maybe this whole
bizarre phenomenon.
Is the reason why all of the
others haven't returned yet.
What have
you done, Azuma?
They were supposed to be
reduced to dead leaves
blown away by the wind.
[BLUENOTE] So now the mighty
Gildarts is nothing but
a powerless joke!
Ha!
I had expected
much more from you, old man.
Where is
all this coming from?
I came here
to show the young ones
how to hone their skills.
You think they're gonna take
me as an authority if I let
some Dark Guild low-life
get the best of me?
My reputation's at stake here,
so I gotta get back up!
Oh yes!
This is what I wanted!
A battle where
we could both soar to
the highest levels
of our fighting skill!
So let me show you
why my name strikes sheer terror
into the hearts of men!
My Black hole!
What kind of
crazy magic is this?
[BLUENOTE] It's an
infinite gravity well.
And nothing can resist its pull!
[GILDARTS]
We'll see about that!
Ready?
Let's fly!!
Come forth!
dark tower of Dingir!
[RUSTYROSE] Turn all your sorrow
onto the foolish fairies.
and return them to the refuse
from whence they came!
What is this spell?
[BIXLOW]
Man, I can't move!
We've all gotten trapped
in this thing!
This sacred ground
you hold so dear will serve
as your graves!
No!
I've got no other choice!
I gotta use my figure eyes.
But that spell won't
work on someone wearing glasses.
I know.
The guy I'm using it
on is too manly for glasses!
I need your help for a second!
Glad to be of service!
Now take that guy down!
What?
Nice one!
Are you Ready Fried!
Here we go!
[FRIED]
Right!
It cracked?
[GILDARTS]
If you really wanna fly.
I can help you out!
He crushed my black
hole with a shattering spell?
How?
Crushing evil spreading truth.
Empyrean!
Dark Écriture!!
Death!!
It seems as though your
magic power has been returned.
Ur's will.
Huh.
You can believe me
or not you know.
It's up to you.
As for me.
I'm taking Zeref
off this island.
Listen.
Hades must fall.
I'm positive that
with Ur's Iced Shell.
He can be defeated
once and for all.
Please Gray.
My mother and I both dreamed
this would one day come to pass.
Please make it happen for us.
[NATSU]
Come on!
Get the lead out!
I can't believe we
all felt so horrible and weak
just a minute ago!
Yeah, speaking of, are
you guys sure that we're totally
back to normal right now.
I mean we don't wanna rush into
anything we're not ready for,
right?
All I really care
about is getting gramps
somewhere safe.
Plus, we won't have any clue
what's going on with the guys
back at camp until we can
see 'em for ourselves!
[HAPPY] I don't know
if I can make it.
I might die of starvation
before we even get there!
[LUCY]
Get over it, cat!
It's not like the rest
of us have been getting
three squares a day, ya know!
Maybe I'll just die from
a sympathy overdose instead.
[NATSU] Actually,
I'm pretty hungry too.
I haven't eaten any kinda
fire since I had to swallow
that nasty stuff that god
slayer bozo was servin' up.
[LUCY] Honestly,
a bite of something
would really help me out.
Cana's heavier than she looks.
[WENDY] Wow, you'd
better be glad she can't
hear you right now.
Because that's kinda rude.
[HAPPY]
See.
I'm not the only one.
[CARLA]
No, this is horrible!
I decided to fly up in
order to get an aerial view
of the island.
The great tree growing
in the middle of it.
Has been snapped in half!
[ALL]
What??
It makes more
sense to me now.
That tree falling must have
something to do with why we all
lost our magic power earlier.
[FRIED] It is commonly known
as the Great Tenrou Tree.
The legends say it blesses
our guild members.
[BIXLOW] Well, the rumor
I've always heard about it.
Is that if you have the Fairy
Tail emblem on your body,
the tree actually
keeps you from dying.
[LEVY]
Really?
That means all our wounded
members will survive.
Yeah, but.
If the Tenrou tree got
knocked over somehow.
Why did we get our
magic power back?
[FRIED] There are many
unanswered questions
at the moment.
[PANTHERLILY] We need to
stay alert and make sure
we completely recover.
[GRAY]
Okay, I'll do it.
You will?
[GRAY]
That's right.
I'll beat Hades.
You know
that Iced Shell is fatal
to whoever casts it.
I'm well aware of that.
I know exactly what
I'll be getting myself into
by doing this.
Thank you.
[GRAY]
Don't.
'Cause I ain't doin' this for
you or for your mother either.
It's for Fairy Tail.
Whoa.
It's a whole lot worse
than I thought it'd be.
Yeah this is awful.
[LUCY] Even Gajeel
and Mira went down.
Don't worry guys, I'll
use my Sky Magic heal them.
[LISANNA]
Hey, Natsu.
Oh, I'm glad
you're okay Lisanna.
Me too, I was
so worried about you.
I appreciate what
you're trying to do, Wendy.
But I'm not sure
you can right now.
Your magic power has
been seriously overtaxed today.
You need to rest
for a little while.
You know
Carla's right, Wendy.
What happened here?
Tell me.
That man over there
attacked us.
And then all of a sudden
we lost our magic power.
Like we were all drained
at the same time.
It was strange.
Fried and Bixlow fought
as hard as they could.
But with everyone
injured, we were already at
such a major disadvantage.
This is bad.
I don't know what
we're gonna do.
Aw, please
don't cry Lisanna.
We are gonna figure
this out, I promise you.
You're right.
I know, I'm sorry, you guys.
[NATSU]
They're gonna pay.
I'll make damn sure of that.
Natsu.
We have to try at least.
And now we can
count Master and Cana among
the injured.
How'd they get
the upper hand like this?
Grimoire Heart's
ship is stationed right off
the shoreline,
just east of here.
I propose this strategy.
That we split our group
into two separate teams.
One team will be offense.
and one defense.
[ULTEAR]
Meldy!
[MELDY]
Oh.
Did you find him?
That man with you.
Is that Zeref?
It is indeed.
It's Lord Zeref.
There's been
a change of plan.
We're leaving the island.
Are you sure that
we should leave so soon?
I still haven't been able
to locate Gray Fullbuster.
[ULTEAR] He is no longer of
your concern now, Meldy.
He's not our enemy.
[GRAY]
I don't get it.
What the hell does Zeref
have to do with Ur's will?
[ULTEAR]
Just hear me out, Gray.
When I was
a little girl my father
was killed by Hades.
My mother kept tabs on
Grimoire Heart, biding her time
until the day came when
she could avenge his death.
After she died.
I found her journal and That's
when I discovered the truth.
That day,
I made a decision that I would
infiltrate Grimoire Heart.
However.
Hades was more powerful
than I'd ever imagined.
My mother perfected the
Iced Shell, because that was
the only way to take him down.
That's why
she learned it?
But Even though her
blood runs through my veins.
I was never able
to master it myself.
As far as I can tell.
that is only spell capable
of defeating Hades.
And I have failed at it.
You needn't trouble
yourself with Zeref.
I will seal him
away, off the island.
Somewhere, that he will
never be found again.
I will keep him
out of Hades' reach.
Please Gray.
My mother and I both dreamed
this would one day come to pass.
Please make it happen for us.
He's not our
enemy in the slightest.
He's our pawn.
I just can't believe
that he actually fell for that
ridiculous story I told him.
What a fool.
If this goes as
planned, I'll get rid of both
Hades and Gray
in one fell swoop.
It almost couldn't have
come together more perfectly!
Get rid of Master Hades?
But why?
[ULTEAR]
With him gone.
We can keep Lord Zeref
entirely to ourselves!
[MELDY] You'd really betray
our master like this?
[ULTEAR] Hades, Gray,
and anyone else I please.
I will have all of them right
in the palm of my hand.
I will crush anyone who
wants to get near Zeref.
He's entirely
in my possession.
Oh, silly me.
I'm getting carried away.
I'm almost certain
that Gray isn't anywhere near
up to the task at hand.
But at least
he can distract Hades'
ever-watchful eye while
we leave with Zeref.
Let's depart before
his eye falls back to us.
Who might this be?
That's Juvia.
Gray's close friend.
What are you doing?
Preparing
to kill her, obviously.
[MELDY]
But she's not a threat!
She's unconscious!
[ULTEAR]
Be quiet.
This will limit Gray's
options for the future.
He can be killed by Hades.
Or die performing
the Iced Shell.
Seeing his dear friend lying
dead on the ground like this
will only drive him
towards the inevitable.
He found us!
[GRAY] I knew somethin'
was rotten with you.
Well well.
Did you?
And when did you
finally catch on?
From the second
you opened your mouth,
I knew everything that came
out of it would be crap.
Is that so?
You were just playing
along the whole time,
trying to figure out what
my true motives were?
Bad boy.
I made a promise.
I swore that I would never try
to use Iced Shell ever again.
[NATSU] If I didn't let you do
it before why would I let you
do it now?
I'm not gonna let you
go out like that.
[GRAY] I don't care if
this is Ur's will or not.
Because I've got
a will all of my own.
And it says my friends and I are
gonna walk the path of life!
[MELDY]
Life?
[ULTEAR]
My my.
I guess you're not so loyal
to your master after all.
I thought I could
count on you to eliminate Hades
for her sake.
It's such a shame.
Here I was, hoping that
I wouldn't have to
fight you myself.
I'm surprised.
That witch loved you even
more than her own daughter.
I'm afraid I might
enjoy killing you so much
my heart will explode with joy!
You need to show some
respect for your mother.
And since she's not around,
I'll have to teach you
that lesson for her!
You're such a fool.
You've made an extremely grave
mistake in threatening me
like that.
For I am the leader
of the Seven Kin of Purgatory!
And scum like you
is no match for me!
♪
[NATSU]
Alright!!
It looks like we took down
all the bad guys around us,
so it's time to
get the big boss!
[HAPPY] Yeah, well, I hate
to break it to ya, Natsu.
But I heard that you're barely
even in the next episode!
[NATSU]
Aw, baloney!
Of course I'm in it,
I'm the main character!
[HAPPY] You've had your
time in the spotlight.
But now you gotta step aside and
let the real star take over.
Me!
[HAPPY and NATSU]
Next Time: Power of Life
[NATSU]
You've had too much catnip, pal.
[HAPPY] Seriously though, I am
all over this next episode!
[NATSU] Yeah, well how come
you're not in the preview, huh?