In the end, humanity
has prevailed,
only because the dragons
chose to intervene.
For I was too much of a coward
to use the Lumen Histoire.
[MAVIS]
No, it wasn't that.
One day,
the time for it will come,
but not quite yet.
Grandeeney you're back!
[GRANDEENEY] Yes child,
we've returned at last.
And Acnologia has been repelled.
Feels pretty awesome
to have a pack of real
live dragons on our side!
Yeah, I'll say.
Weren't there like, thousands of
those Face things out there?
There were, but these
dragons wiped 'em out.
Friggin' amazing.
I'm proud of you, for
destroying that Face.
Thanks, but...
Carla did the hard part.
[GAJEEL grunts]
[PANTHERLILY]
So that's him?
That's Metalicana?
[LEVY]
He's your dad?
[METALICANA] You still look
like you just swallowed rust.
So do you!
[STING]
I don't get it.
I remember killing you.
So how can you be here?
I need to ask you the
same question, Skiadrum.
How are you still alive?
[WEISSLOGIA]
We altered your memories.
In order to help
you grow strong.
[SKIADRUM]
It was an experiment of ours.
One Igneel was against.
We raised you both
as Dragon Slayers.
And to complete your upbringing,
we gave you the experience
of slaying dragons.
[WEISSLOGIA]
However,
it's incorrect to say
that we're still alive.
Uh?
[GRANDEENEY]
In the truest sense,
we've been dead for
quite some time.
[gasps]
[GRANDEENEY]
Many years ago,
Acnologia used his
Dragon Slayer magic
to tear our spirits
from our bodies.
So we had three reasons
for residing within you.
Please understand.
We did it to defeat Acnologia,
and prevent you
from transforming.
But it was also the only
way we had to survive.
[WENDY]
You mean...?
[SKIADRUM] Now that
we've left your bodies,
there's no way for us to return.
The demonstration of
power we just gave
will also be our last.
We hope you can understand why
we had to remain in hiding
until the time was right.
[ROGUE]
Uh.
[METALICANA]
Even the mighty Igneel
was unable to defeat Acnologia.
However, it must be
said that Igneel
fought from the very
brink of death.
When you tell tales
of this day,
do not let that sully the
Fire Dragon King's name.
[GAJEEL]
Hm?
[METALICANA]
None among us had his courage,
or felt the depth of his
compassion for humanity.
[NATSU]
I'm sorry, dad.
You gave me a job, and I failed.
So I can't hold it against
you that you left.
But I had so many questions.
[NATSU]
Stay.
I searched for you for so long.
I want you to see
what I've become.
I've learned to write.
And I can cook my own food.
I made the best friends.
I've joined the best
guild there is.
Igneel.
Dad.
I have so much more
to say to you!
So don't go!
[GRANDEENEY]
We've only told you a fraction
of what we would if
there were time,
but I'm afraid there's not.
This is goodbye, Wendy.
You're leaving me?
Sweet girl.
The road you'll face
is fraught with peril.
But I've seen you gain
the strength to walk it.
[WENDY]
No, I can't, Grandeeney.
Not without you!
[GAJEEL]
Let's see 'em off, kid.
With our heads held high.
[METALICANA exhales]
[GRANDEENEY]
Farewell, Humans.
Once, very long ago,
there was terrible strife
between our kind and yours.
It warms my heart to
know that in the end,
we part in friendship.
[WEISSLOGIA]
The era of dragons has ended.
We leave this world
for you to protect.
[SKIADRUM] The power of man
shall pave the future,
for that we are thankful.
[GRANDEENEY]
Four hundred years ago,
a Magna Carta pact was made
between human and dragon-kind.
Now, though we are leaving,
we shall not forsake it!
We dragons shall continue
to watch over you!
Forever!
Please don't leave me!
[GRANDEENEY]
I love you Wendy. Always.
[METALICANA] You should
get that face checked out.
[GAJEEL] Way to ruin the
moment, ya old rustbucket!
[GAJEEL]
Hmph. I'll miss you, too.
Weisslogia. Thanks
for everything.
Rest well.
You can't be gone.
[IGNEEL] Cut it out with the
damn waterworks, will you?
[IGNEEL]
Come on, Natsu.
I taught you what to do
when you feel like this.
Have you forgotten?
[NATSU]
I remember.
[IGNEEL]
Then prove it.
Get on your feet.
[NATSU]
Kay.
[IGNEEL] I have been with
you every step of the way,
and nothing has
made me more proud
than seeing what you've done.
[IGNEEL]
Keep growing.
Know that I'll always
live in your heart.
Show me the fire that
burns within you.
I will.
I'm gonna work even harder!
I'm gonna get even stronger!
And when I do,
I'm gonna take down Acnologia!
[IGNEEL]
That's the way.
Speak of the future.
[IGNEEL] That's where the
power of life truly lies.
[LUCY]
It's been a week since then.
The war with Tartaros
left us all with wounds.
The kind that leave scars.
Magnolia took a lot of damage.
Our Guild Hall was reduced
to a pile of rubble.
But apart from the
destruction here,
the Faces devastated cities
across the continent.
[LUCY]
And what cuts the deepest,
is all the loved ones we lost.
[MIRAJANE]
Well,
so what now?
Time to start rebuilding again?
I suppose.
It's gonna be tough.
The townspeople fixed it
up for us the last time.
Yeah, somethin' tells me
we'll have to do it ourselves.
I shouldn't be here.
I really don't have the right.
This wasn't your fault, Elfman.
[MAKAROV]
None of this is anyone's fault.
Perhaps it's a signal.
One to mark the end of an era.
[MIRAJANE gasps]
[BIXLOW]
Geez.
Guy couldn't be more
reckless if he tried.
I talked to Porlyusica earlier.
She told me that it's a
miracle he even survived.
He is gonna wake up
eventually, right?
Of course he is, stupid.
[FRIED exhales]
I'm a failure.
I pledged to be by his side,
to give him support.
But all I did was
lay writhing in pain.
While he stood up and
fought to save us.
I don't deserve him.
I don't deserve to live!
That's nonsense.
Laxus has always been
stronger than us.
Yeah. It totally sucks,
but there's nothin' we
coulda done about it.
If you don't get that he's
out of your league by now,
you're probably a lost cause.
[EVERGREEN]
Hey, stop it!
I'm sorry, Loxus! Farewell!
[EVERGREEN, BIXLOW yelp]
Chill out man! I was just
screwin' with ya, all right?
[EVERGREEN]
Calm down, Fried!
[EVERGREEN, FRIED,
BIXLOW chattering]
[LAXUS gasps]
[BIXLOW]
Uh? Hey buddy.
It's good to see you
up and at 'em again.
Are you feeling better?
Not really.
[FRIED]
What about my feelings?
I've been sick.
Sick worrying about you.
Going off to fight Tempester,
in that condition.
Without even bothering
to wake me up.
I would've come.
[EVERGREEN]
Sure you would've...
Just be happy he's
back, will ya?
I'm pathetic.
[BIXLOW]
Whoa there!
[EVERGREEN]
What's gotten into you?!
[LAXUS]
I'm not nearly good enough.
[FRIED]
Uh.
[LAXUS]
You three are the world to me;
I can't keep you safe.
Not as I am now.
Amazing!
My hair looks exactly
like it did before!
Always down to do a do, baby.
Thank you for the hook up.
I appreciate it.
[LUCY]
Glad to help!
The other look was interesting,
but I think this
suits you better.
Since I'm here,
how about a sweet new
hairdo for you, baby?
[LUCY]
Hmm. I could go longer.
[WENDY]
I'm sure it would look nice!
[CANCER]
If by nice, you mean hot.
[LUCY chuckles nervously]
How has Wendy been
handling everything?
About how you'd expect.
What's that mean?
She's putting on a
brave face for now.
[CARLA]
And she's improving.
How's Gajeel?
Him?
Why don't you take
a look for yourself?
Um, Gajeel?
Maybe you should go
home and take a nap.
You're snoring in public.
[snores]
Or not.
[WENDY, LUCY laugh]
It hurt them.
Havin' to say their goodbyes.
I'm worried about Natsu, too.
He'll be fine. I've
no doubt about that.
[CARLA]
Oh?
He does have Happy
with him, after all.
[NATSU]
All right, Happy.
How much dough do
we have stashed?
We've got one hundred'n
thirty thousand Jewel.
[NATSU]
Hm. So we're kinda poor.
Aye sir.
We'd'a been pretty
friggin' loaded
if somebody hadn't
stolen our safe.
We had enough jewel for
like ten years of fish.
Oh, well.
We'll make it work somehow!
Aye!
[NATSU sighs] But this
letter is the real issue.
[JUVIA]
Hey.
I'm really sorry
for interrupting.
Juvia?
Why the hell did you
follow me out here?
Forgive me, but I had to come.
[JUVIA]
You see.
There's something...
something wrong I did
that you deserve to know about.
The necromancer.
The one who was
controlling your father,
it was me who defeated him.
So it's my fault that...
[GRAY]
You did what?
[JUVIA]
I'm sorry.
I realize... that
after what I've done,
I've lost the right to love you.
Because I know
that you love him.
And I killed him.
[GRAY growls]
[JUVIA gasps]
It was you?!
You freed him.
[GRAY]
Thank you.
[JUVIA]
Gray.
[GRAY cries]
[GRAY]
I'm so sorry.
[GRAY cries]
[JUVIA]
You're so warm.
[ERZA grunts]
[ERZA] Those memories
will haunt me to my grave,
but will they always
make me tremble?
Betrayed.
Bound.
Beaten and shamed.
Perhaps they broke me after all,
and I was just too
blind to see it.
[footsteps]
[JELLAL]
You'll be okay, Erza.
[ERZA gasps]
I'm sure of it.
You know very well just how
weak, and strong, people can be.
[JELLAL] All you need to do
is follow the path of light.
Like you always have.
[JELLAL] And we shall follow
the path of darkness.
For that's where
we'll find Zeref.
These outfits are lame.
Stop your complaining.
[JELLAL]
It is possible though,
that our paths will
someday cross.
I wonder why he's tryin'
to act so cool about it.
How 'bout we exchange
our theories later?
Is it love?! It must be!
[JELLAL]
And when that day does come,
I hope your light will
wash out our shadows.
Until then... move forward.
[ERZA]
My trembling has stopped,
for now.
[MALE SABERTOOTH A]
Check it out, everyone!
Sting and Rogue're back!
[FEMALE SABERTOOTH 5A]
So are Lector and Frosch!
And one more!
Lady Minerva's with them!
[SABERTOOTH murmuring]
Hey there, it's good
to have you back.
Yeah.
[ROGUE, STING chuckle]
It's good to be home.
[MALE SABERTOOTH B]
M'lady has returned!
[SABERTOOTH cheers]
[FEMALE SABERTOOTH B]
We missed you, Minerva!
[MINERVA]
I'm... I'm really home!
[MALE SABERTOOTH 5C]
She's crying!
[MALE SABERTOOTH D]
Think it got cold in hell, too?
[YUKINO] Stop it!
You're embarrassing her!
[DORANBOLT sighs]
Well, I did as you asked.
Everyone who heard you
say 'you-know-what,'
got their mind wiped.
[MAKAROV]
Hm.
[DORANBOLT groans]
And, I know what's next.
You want me to erase my own
memories now, don't ya?
I can do it,
but I hate messin'
with my own memory.
[MAKAROV]
Then don't.
You've earned my trust and more.
[DORANBOLT]
Hm?
[MAKAROV]
Mest Gryder.
Your task is complete.
Uh... What the--?
[DORANBOLT]
What was that for?!
Have you lost your mind?!
[DORANBOLT]
Uh?!
The hell is this?!
How did I get a
Fairy Tail emblem?!
Start talkin'!
You've always had that emblem.
We concealed it when
you began your mission.
Then, you erased
your own memory,
and infiltrated
the Magic Council.
[screams]
You're a good man. Fully
devoted to the mission.
Willing to sacrifice
your own identity
to ensure the safety of
the guild you serve.
[DORANBOLT]
Okay, whoa! Slow down!
What are you saying here?!
You think I infiltrated
the Council for Fairy Tail?!
Well then what about the time
when I infiltrated Fairy
Tail for the Council?!
This is pure insanity!
[gasping]
This is exactly why I told you
you didn't need to
erase your memories.
Pull yourself together, man.
[DORANBOLT]
Uh. So this is for real?
Yes, but no matter.
It's coming to a close now.
What do you mean?
[MAKAROV] I mean that we've
come to the end of an era.
It's time I let the kids go out
and find their own paths.
Fairy Tail will not rebuild.
I'm disbanding it.
[LUCY gasps]
I can sense a presence within.
I bet it's Natsu
and Happy! Heh, heh.
All right you two, party's
over, you're busted!
Wait... What?
[LUCY gasps]
A letter?
[LUCY] Wow. Someone writes
even worse than Erza.
[gasps] What?! No way!
What the heck are
they thinking?!
[NATSU] Me and Happy are goin'
on a lil trainin' mission.
Be back in a year or so.
Tell everybody bye
for us, will ya?
Thanks Lucy! See ya later!
[LUCY panting]
[LUCY] How can you just
up and leave me alone
for an entire frickin' year?
How dumb are you, Natsu?!
[LUCY]
Can't you see?!
[LUCY] Did you even think of
what this would do to me?!
I'll find E.N.D.
And then I'll take him down.
You will.
[MAKAROV]
Spread your wings, Fairy Tail!
[NATSU]
Sorry, everyone.
But I've gotta get way stronger
before I can show my face again.
[NATSU]
So I can keep all of you safe.
Perhaps you can
surpass me. Try...
Natsu. Or should I say
Etherious Natsu Dragneel.
[MAVIS] In the wake of
the war against Tartaros,
Fairy Tail is suddenly disbanded
by order of Master Makarov.
As that era comes to a close,
the story of its creation
is at last revealed.
It's a tale of hope
and friendship.
One woven by a barefoot girl
who had nothing but
a dream in her heart.
That girl was me.
Next time:
"The Fairy In Your Heart."
Beyond the end,
you'll find the beginning.