[ASCA] I know this place!
I remember all the pretty snow,
and laughing under
the moon and stars!
There was the
funny flying snowman!
I wanted to
play with him so bad!
Mommy and daddy
were there with me!
That made me so happy!
And then the snowman
banged the drum!
He banged it so hard,
we all went flying
into the sky with him!
It made us
all laugh and laugh!
It was so much fun!
[ASCA laughing]
[ASCA] Bye-bye, mommy!
Bye-bye, daddy!
[BISCA, ALZACK]
Bye-bye, darlin'!
Take real good care
of our lil' dumplin' okay?
Sure! Don't you worry!
Don't forget to bring
me back lotsa presents!
We won't!
Love you!
[NATSU] All right, kiddo.
Wanna go get some juice?
Yeah!
[HAPPY]
What a Pure Heart Weaves!
Super yummy! Wow!
I wanna drink another one!
Uh, I don't think so.
You gotta be real careful.
Too much of that stuff
might make you wet the--
Shut up.
Don't say another word about it.
You'll hurt her feelings.
You'll whet your appetite!
And then you'll
be way too hungry
to have any kinda fun today!
[laughs nervously]
[ASCA] You were
gonna say "wet the bed,"
but big girls don't do that!
He's got to be the
most clueless person
I've ever met.
You're a really lucky
little girl, ya know.
Not everyone knows
someone as fun as Natsu!
Yeah, and he even said
that he's gonna
buy me some cake, too!
I did?
Do you even sell
cake at the bar, Mira?
Mommy and daddy
got some for me!
Well we normally have cake,
but we sold the
last one earlier today.
Aww!
I'm sorry about that.
Will ya take a rain check?
You can just go to
the bakery across town
and get some there instead!
You gotta be crazy if you think
I'm gonna go through all that!
Don't worry, guys!
I'd be more than happy
to bake a cake for her!
Yeah?
I didn't know you knew
how to do stuff like that.
Well, I've only
made a few of them,
so it's not really
something I do all the time.
But I'll sure try!
While there's a slim chance
it'll be anywhere near yummy,
it might be edible
at the very least.
[chair sliding]
If you insist,
I will gladly join you
on this quest for cake!
Say what now?
Nobody was even talking to her.
But if we are to
take on this endeavor,
we must ensure they are the
finest cakes in all of Fiore.
Do you understand?
Huh? Uh, okay!
I think the real truth is
that you just want to
eat some, too, don't you?
But to achieve our goal,
we need to harvest some
Maximum Sweet Strawberries.
The rarest kind that exist.
The Legends say they only grow
once every ten thousand years.
She's completely
in her own little world.
I shall embark
at once to find them!
Now you're gonna leave
to go pick strawberries?
[ERZA] Look alive, Pantherlily!
I'm gonna need your help!
Say what?
Why do you need me?
Because, that's why!
Sounds like a good time to me.
So let's hit the road!
You're s'posed to be
playing with me today, 'member?
Uh... Of course I remember!
Okay.
I guess I should get started
making some sponge cakes!
And I'll start whipping
up some cream for them.
Whoa, you mean you can
actually make food, too?
Did you say something?
I mean, that sounds yummy!
Our success depends on you!
Come on, Lily. Let's get moving!
What? You're serious?
[PANTHERLILY] Put me down!
[LUCY] Are Erza and Lily
going on a job together?
That's a weird team, huh?
They're picking strawberries!
Yeah? Never woulda guessed that!
[NATSU] All right,
the rules are simple!
Whichever one of us
hits the target the most times
is the winner!
I got it! Pow, pow, pow!
[LUCY] Hey, what are
you guys doing over here?
A little
sharpshooting contest.
We're gonna see
if he's better with fire
than she is with a toy gun.
I like ya,
but ya ain't gonna beat me!
But if I do, ya gotta
do whatever I tell ya to!
All right, you're on!
You don't have
to take it so seriously.
She's just a little kid.
I'm not gonna go easy
on her just 'cause she's young.
Losin' just ain't my style!
[laughs]
Could you be
any more immature?
Get real, you know
Natsu is just a big ol' kid.
Let's do this!
[ASCA]
Clippity-clop! Clippity-clop!
Giddy up, little horsey,
we got bandits to chase!
He knew the rules.
You gotta start makin'
some horsey noises, Natsu!
[neighs awkwardly]
Come on, you can
do better than that!
[neighs awkwardly]
That'll teach him
to never play a player.
Well, considering what
both her parents are like,
she was probably shooting guns
while she was in the womb!
Yeah, I'd bet you're
right about that one.
Where are her parents, anyway?
They went on a job.
And for some reason
they asked Natsu to babysit
while they were
gone for the day.
[neighs awkwardly]
--You're killin' me, kid!
--Okay, Mister Horsey!
I want you to gallop all
the way to the Southgate Park!
You're gonna make
me do this in public?
Oh yeah! So giddy-up, Natsu!
And this is why
I'm scared of children.
You lost fair and square, pal.
So just grin and bear it.
Okily doke, m'lady,
the park it is!
Yay!
You got precious cargo there,
so be careful!
There's been a
buncha ne'er do wells
causin' trouble in town lately.
Keep your eyes on her.
Well, they're
gonna be really sorry
if they try and mess with us!
[ASCA laughing]
Pow! Pow!
Oh, ya got me!
--Pow pow pow!
--But I'm still goin'!
[laughing]
[ASCA] Pow!
So why did I
come along, again?
Because Natsu
is babysitting her.
And that's scary.
Let me teach you how to shoot
since you're so bad at it.
Oh, you think
you're hot stuff?
You're just a kid! Oww!
Hang on!
Stop right where you are!
Stand still for me!
Huh? On this thing?
[ASCA] Yup! Now jump in!
Why the heck would
you make me do that?
Because you promised me.
You said you'd do
whatever I wanted, 'member?
[ASCA] Hey!
I wanna go on some jobs
with you guys!
Sorry, but
that's not happening.
Yeah, you're still
way too little.
You're not any
bigger than me, Happy!
We're out having fun,
so why would ya wanna work?
Because there's
something I really wanna buy!
So I need money!
So let's go on a job!
Let's go right now!
Geez, this kid is so pushy!
I don't know.
We'd definitely need
to ask your mom and dad
before we went and
did something like that.
But... But Natsu promised me.
Okay, fine!
So let's head back to the guild
and check the request board!
Do you mean it?
Just leave everything to me!
[ASCA] Yeehaw! Thank you!
[HAPPY] There's gotta be a job
we can take the rugrat on...
I got a bunch
of 'em to choose from!
[ASCA laughing]
[NATSU] Nice work!
Let's see here...
I don't even
understand this one.
What exactly do they need?
Whatever it is,
I don't think little Asca
can do it, anyway.
[HAPPY] Look.
I know just what
and who they need!
Huh?
Uh, aww. This is gonna suck.
Open...
Gate of the Water Bearer!
Aquarius!
Thanks a lot, mermaid lady!
I have never been
so humiliated in my life.
You owe me.
I'm sorry.
But there's nobody else
that could fill in
for a broken fountain.
This is so romantic.
From the first time
we met at this plaza,
I've wanted to ask you
this question.
And I pray that
you don't say no.
My darling girl,
will you marry me?
Oh, yes, I will!
And to make things worse,
I gotta stand here and watch
this sappy B.S. all day?
I know it's not ideal,
but it's not gonna last forever!
This fountain is beautiful
cause you're so pretty!
Okay, fine.
But don't expect me
to do this ever again!
[OLD WOMAN 219A] I haven't been
able to cook a thing for days.
Fire it up real good, Natsu!
I thought a
delivery job would be
something you and I
could do together!
Yeehaw!
So since we've
come all this way,
where are all of these
magnum sweeper special--
I'm sure you mean the
Maximum Sweet Strawberries.
The legends say
they're somewhere
in this mountain range.
Are you kidding me?
How are we gonna find them?
Watch and learn.
Now, requip!
What in the heck is that getup?
Some kind of strawberry armor?
You could say that.
[PANTHERLILY]
It looks hard to move in.
The purpose of
this particular armor
is to emit the sweet
fragrance of strawberries.
Do you understand
what that will do?
[distant rumbling]
Oh! A woman that
smells like strawberries!
These creatures can't
resist women or berries,
so we shall ask them.
That's your plan, is it?
Correct!
So apprehend those stinky,
love struck apes at once!
I get it!
That's why you brought me here!
Geez.
That's all you had to say!
Yah!
The throes of battle are
impossible for me to resist!
Strawberry Armor:
Berry Sweet Dreams!
What a sweet defeat.
[ERZA] Now...
I've heard tales that
you mountain-dwelling Vulcans
possess important information
regarding the secret location
of Maximum Sweet Strawberries!
You'd be wise to share.
Yes ma'am.
[ASCA] Wow!
I can't believe
how many bills
we were able to rake
in just one afternoon.
Going on a bunch
of those little jobs
really adds up quickly.
Just let her have it,
Natsu, she's just a kid.
Now I can finally
buy what I want!
And what's that?
[LUCY] Something from here?
Wow!
[giggling]
What is it, anyway?
It looks like a really
pretty snow globe to me.
Is it some kinda lacrima?
It's so cool!
Yep, it's got mommy
and daddy's memories in it!
That thing's got what now?
So what's it
doing in a pawnshop?
I don't know.
But one time we were all
walking by that store's window
and they started
talking about it.
I can't believe
it's actually still here.
I know.
We sure have come
a long way since then.
[ALZACK] It's kind of
a beautiful memory now.
Aw, how sweet.
The whole reason
you wanted to buy it
is so you could give it
back to your mom and dad!
Mmm-hmm!
What a good girl.
Come here,
ya little sweetheart!
I'm gettin a little
misty-eyed over here!
Not me, bro.
Lucy?
When are you and Natsu
finally gonna kiss each other?
Say what?
Mommy and Daddy are
kissing all of the time!
[LUCY] That's great...
But we're not
your mom and dad, kid!
Give her a smooch, Natsu!
Right on the lips!
You gotta do
what she says, buddy!
You're way too
young to ask for that!
Yeah, I'm sorry
to let you down and all,
but that is totally
out of the question!
But you promised
me that you'd do
anything I asked you to do.
Well, it's not like
it'll kill us or anything.
Yeah, you're right!
Wait a second,
it's not my health
I'm concerned about!
Whoa...
You're actually serious
about this, aren't you?
And this is why
I'm scared of children.
That's good enough, I guess!
It's gone!
[ORCA WINGS laughing]
Sorry, little girl.
But this belongs to the
Orca Wing sky pirates now!
Who in the heck
are those jerks?
Sky pirates?
These must be the ones that
Wakaba and that other guy
were trying to warn us about!
Give it back to me!
Please!
That's Mommy and Daddy's!
It has their memories!
You can't take it away!
[WENDY] Mm!
I sure hope this cake
tastes as good as it smells!
Well, the whipped cream
is just about ready to go.
All we need are strawberries!
Erza's getting those for us.
I wonder if
she's found them yet.
Oh my!
The secret strawberry grove!
I'm guessing those must be
the Maximum Sweet Strawberries!
That'd be great if they were,
but those are just
regular giant strawberries.
If you really wanna
find the Maximum Sweet one
that you've been looking for,
it's right down there.
Excellent!
Now harvest this rare delicacy
and deliver it straight
to Fairy Tail ASAP!
If we do that,
will you please stop
ordering us around?
Yeah, baby!
I betcha this lacrima here
will sell for a boatload of
jewel down in Hargeon!
It's our lucky day!
Take me up, Happy!
[HAPPY] My poor little
beak's been tainted.
Grow up, ya big sissy.
Give it back, meanie!
Give it back right now!
You're gonna need
way more firepower,
ya little brat!
I got him.
I just keep shooting at him
but he still won't stop!
I want mommy and
daddy's memories back.
They need them.
He can't just take them.
[sobbing]
Why are you doing that?
I can't see the bad guys!
Hey! Stop that!
Shh!
Okay, Asca!
Fire off four in a row!
[ORCA WINGS yelling]
You got all of 'em!
That's some awfully nice
shootin' ya did there, Asca!
Nothin' but bull's-eyes!
Way to go, lil' sharpshooter!
[ASCA] Thanks!
I'll be.
I'm not gonna go easy
on her just 'cause she's young.
Losin' just ain't my style!
So he did
let her win earlier.
All that talk was for her sake.
What a sweet guy!
[HAPPY] My beak...
It's been poisoned.
[NATSU] All right!
We'll be taking
this thing back now.
No way.
You can't just take somebody's
stuff from 'em like that!
Oh yeah?
You ain't seen the last of us!
We'll be back! You'll be sorry!
[screaming]
No doubt about it,
you're Alzack and Bisca's kid!
And I wouldn't be
surprised if she's a better shot
than either of her parents!
Pow!
[NATSU, LUCY, ASCA]
We're back!
Gotta say, you guys
have impeccable timing!
They're just about to put the
finishing touches on the cake!
We have cake?
Yeah, I almost
forgot about that!
Welcome back!
So have they finished
making my cake yet?
Almost!
[ERZA] No, not there yet!
These cakes
won't be Fiore's finest
unless the cream
instantly melts in your mouth!
We can't give up till
we've reached that goal!
We're working on it, boss!
I mean, uh, Miss Erza!
Well, will this be good enough?
Let's see...
I'll give it a taste-test.
It's melting splendidly!
This flavor mixed with the
Maximum Sweet Strawberry
may prove too much for
my tastebuds to handle!
All right! Prepare for plating!
I'm so happy that we
actually finished it in time!
[ERZA] Now, Asca,
will you do the honors?
Oh, this looks so amazing!
Hurry up and eat it
before it starts to melt away!
Just go on and shove it in!
That's the yummiest!
Oh, I'm so relieved
that you like it, Asca!
You deserve it
for all your work today!
[ERZA] Mmmm. That's nice.
So it was yummy.
Huh. That's good to know.
I can practically
imagine the flavor.
[laughing nervously]
I knew it.
She really just wanted
some for herself all along.
[ASCA] Mommy! Daddy!
I'm so glad to see you!
--Hey there, darlin'!
So were you a good girl?
[ASCA] Yeah!
[BISCA]
We got you a little present!
Really?
Thank you so much!
And I have a
present for you, too.
Hey, thanks again, Natsu.
I appreciate you
lookin' after the kiddo.
It's cool. We had
a really awesome time!
Until that horrible
thing happened at the end.
I got this present for you.
No way...
How in the heck
did you get that?
With her own money.
She went on a
couple of jobs with us.
Yep!
Oh, it was nothing
dangerous though, really!
[ALZACK, BISCA chuckling]
This here was the
reward from the first job
Bisca and I went on together.
It meant a lot to us.
Sure is pretty.
Gorgeous.
Well if the thing's
that important,
why'd you end up selling it?
Something more
important came up.
This brings back some memories!
You sold it 'cause
you didn't want it?
No, sugar.
We sold it because it
was the only choice we had.
Huh?
You'll understand
one of these days, punkin'.
[ALZACK] Let's head on home!
[ASCA] Okay!
Thanks again, you guys.
It really means a lot to us.
We appreciate it.
[ASCA] Bye!
Let's do more jobs
together sometime, okay?
Yeah, sure! Sounds like fun!
[ASCA] Hey, guess what!
Natsu and Happy kissed!
[ALZACK]
Wow! I knew they were close.
[laughing]
[BISCA] This takes me back.
[ALZACK] Yeah. Our baby.
Fast asleep while the two of us
were talkin' about
how much we loved her.
Let's just borrow the
money from our guildmates!
I ain't gonna
ask them for money!
What then?
We can't afford her medicine!
Just hang on.
Please, darlin'.
Memories are nice, I guess.
But we can make
a lot more of those.
We gotta do it for her!
\Please get better.
[BISCA]
Mommy and daddy are always
gonna be here for ya',
sweetheart.
[HAPPY] Hey, Natsu.
Does the number four hundred
thirteen mean anything to you?
[NATSU] No, why?
[HAPPY] Because earlier
I heard Juvia singing,
"today is day
four hundred and thirteen!"
[NATSU]
I guess it's something special.
[HAPPY] Oh!
Maybe it's a day
when you gotta eat
four hundred-thirteen fish,
or something!
[NATSU] Naw, probably not!
[HAPPY] I got it!
It's a day when you eat four
hundred-thirteen types of fish!
[NATSU] You're
really reachin' there, bro!
[HAPPY, NATSU]
Next Time: 413 Days!
Well, then what kind of
fish-eating day is it?
[NATSU] Just let go
of the fish idea.