- HEY, GUYS.  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Narrator: THIS IS THE
MYSTERIOUS EAST FOREST
FOUND IN MAGNOLIA.
A PLACE OVERFLOWING
WITH MAGICAL POWER,
OF WHICH MANY TALES ARE TOLD.
- OH, COME ON.  I HAVE A NOVEL
TO WRITE, YOU KNOW.
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO
DRAG ME ALONG
ON YOUR STUPID
FISHING TRIP?
- STOP COMPLAINING.
BESIDES, YOU JUST SAID
YOU HAD WRITER'S BLOCK,
DIDN'T YOU?
- AYE.
AND NOTHING CAN GET
YOUR CREATIVE JUICES FLOWING
LIKE A CHANGE OF PACE.
- YEAH, BUT WHY DOES IT
HAVE TO BE FISHING?
- 'CAUSE FISH IS MY VERY
MOST FAVORITEST FOOD, OF COURSE.
- YOU'RE MISSING THE POINT.
I'M ASKING WHY
I HAVE TO FISH
FOR YOUR FAVORITE FOOD.
- WHOA.  I GOT ONE.
- WATCH OUT.
LOOKS LIKE A WHOPPER!
- LEAVE IT TO ME.
( shouts )
- IT'S HUGE!
- Happy: UPPA!
- Lucy:
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
- ( chuckles )
LOOK AT THAT.
JUST LIKE THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
- ( theme music playing )
- FISHY WISHY,
NUMMY YUMMY,
GET IN MY TUMMY!
UPPA!  YUM!
- I KNEW YOU WERE IMMATURE,
BUT THIS IS A NEW LOW.
- ( screams )
- OH, YEAH.
THAT LOOKS TASTY.
- YOU RUINED IT!
FISH TASTES BETTER
IF YOU EAT IT RAW.
- WHY WOULD I DO THAT
WHEN IT ONLY TAKES A SEC
TO GRILL IT UP?
- 'CAUSE THAT'S HOW I
WANTED TO EAT IT.
- I GOT IT,
SO I EAT IT MY WAY.
IF YOU'RE GONNA COMPLAIN,
GO CATCH YOUR OWN.
- DON'T DO IT!
- EW.  HE'S EATING IT
BONES AND ALL.
- EHH.
- ( sighs )
MAN, THAT HIT THE SPOT.
- HOW COULD YOU?
FINE! OUR FRIENDSHIP
IS OVER, NATSU!
- YOU'RE QUITE THE DRAMA QUEEN,
AREN'T YOU?
- HMM.
- YOU GONNA FOLLOW HIM?
OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
KEEP UP THAT TOUGH GUY ACT
AND YOU'LL NEVER GET
THE GIRLS TO LIKE YOU.
- ( gasps )
- ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
- GO APOLOGIZE--
- JUST SHUT YOUR MOUTH FOR ONCE.
- WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT?
SCARY.
- ( gasps )
- Narrator:
THE FAIRY TAIL ARCHIVES
WHERE THE GUILD'S
RECORDS ARE STORED.
- HEY, MIRA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP THERE?
- JUST A BIT OF REORGANIZING,
THAT'S ALL.
- OH, I CAN HELP WITH THAT.
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO?
- YEAH.
I'M GOOD WITH BORING STUFF.
- MM-HMM!
- AND THEN HE JUST
STORMED OFF.
WHAT A JERK, RIGHT?
- ( giggles )
MAYBE.
BUT THAT'S WHAT
MAKES HIM SO CUTE.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- OF COURSE.
- YOU'RE ATTRACTED TO
NATSU'S BOYISH CHARMS TOO,
AREN'T YOU?
- WHAT?!
AH-- NO!
- LUCY.
- ( laughing )
- YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I GUESS LADDERS
AREN'T MY STRONG POINT.
I FOUND AND OLD PAINTING.
- ( chuckles )
I REMEMBER THAT.
- IS THIS EVERYONE
WHEN THEY WERE KIDS?
- IT SURE IS.
- Lucy:
THIS MUST BE GRAY.
AND WHO'S THAT
NEXT TO HIM?
CANA?
WHOA, MACAO AND WAKABA?
THEY LOOK SO YOUNG!
( chuckles )
OH, I'D RECOGNIZE
THAT SPIKY HEAD ANYWHERE.
NATSU HASN'T CHANGED A BIT.
AND WHAT'S WITH
THE LITTLE BLUE DRAGON?
- THAT'S HAPPY.
- ( gasps )
I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU EVEN KNOW THIS,
BUT HOW DID NATSU AND HAPPY
FIRST MEET, ANYWAY?
- LET ME THINK.
WHEN THAT PICTURE WAS PAINTED,
I HADN'T BEEN A MEMBER
OF FAIRY TAIL
FOR VERY LONG MYSELF.
THE TIME SURE HAS FLOWN BY.
- Makarov: HEY, NATSU!
- HE WENT OUT.
- SOMETHING ABOUT A FIGHT.
- I'LL SHOW YOU!
- LET'S SEE YOU TRY.
- SHUT YOUR FACE!
- Mirajane: BACK THEN,
NATSU AND GRAY WERE
LITTLE BALLS OF HATE.
THEY'D FIGHT EVERY TIME
THEY RAN INTO EACH OTHER.
- Lucy: DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE MUCH HAS CHANGED.
- ( both grunt )
- FLAME-BRAINED LIZARD!
- UNDIE-FLASHING FREAK!
- ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH OUT OF YOU.
- Mirajane: OF COURSE, THERE WAS
ALWAYS SOMEONE TO BREAK THEM UP.
- Lucy:
LET ME GUESS, ERZA.
- MIND YOUR OWN
BUSINESS FOR ONCE.
- YOU WANT A PIECE
OF ME TOO, YOU JERK?
- IF YOU INSIST.
- ( both shout )
( both grunt )
- NOW BEHAVE.
NO MORE POINTLESS FIGHTING
FROM YOU TWO.
- YOU JUST GOT LUCKY.
- I'LL WIN NEXT TIME.
- Mirajane: NATSU WAS ALWAYS
GETTING INTO FIGHTS LIKE THAT.
OF COURSE, HE ACTED LIKE
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTED,
BUT SOMETIMES I'D CATCH HIM
WITH A SAD LOOK ON HIS FACE.
THEN ONE DAY...
- ( grunting )
AAH!
STUPID ERZA AND GRAY.
YOU STINK!
( grunts )
AAH!
THAT DIDN'T HURT AT ALL.
OH, WHAT THE HECK?
( chuckles )
HEY, YOU GUYS!
CHECK OUT THIS AWESOME EGG
I JUST FOUND.
- WHERE IN BLAZES
DID YOU PICK UP THAT THING?
- I FOUND IT IN
THE EAST FOREST.
- THE EAST FOREST?
- LOOK AT THAT.
GUESS YOU'RE GOOD
FOR SOMETHING AFTER ALL, HUH?
GONNA FRY IT UP FOR US?
- GRAY, YOUR CLOTHES!
- ( gasps )
- I AIN'T GONNA FRY THIS.
CAN'T YOU SEE IT'S
A DRAGON'S EGG?
I'M GONNA HATCH IT.
- YOU SURE?
- LOOK AT THE MARKS
ON THE OUTSIDE OF IT.
THEY LOOK JUST LIKE
DRAGON CLAWS, RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
- SO ANYWAY, GRAMPS,
WHY DON'T YOU HATCH
THE DRAGON WITH A SPELL?
- GAH.  DON'T BE A FOOL.
USING MAGIC
FOR SUCH A PURPOSE
WOULD DISHONOR
THE MIRACLE OF LIFE.
YOU SEE, LIFE IS
BORN FROM LOVE
AND LOVE ALONE.
NO SPELL CAN
TRANSCEND THAT POWER.
- UH...
SORRY, GRAMPS.
I DON'T THINK I'M FOLLOWING YOU.
- ( sighs ) YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
WHEN YOU GROW UP.
- HE'S SAYING THAT IF
YOU WANT IT TO HATCH,
YOU HAVE TO WORK HARD TO
MAKE IT HAPPEN ON YOUR OWN.
SINCE YOU USUALLY JUST
BURN AND BREAK THINGS ALL DAY,
IT MIGHT BE NICE
TO TRY SOMETHING
MORE PRODUCTIVE FOR ONCE.
- ERZA!
- I DIDN'T HEAR YOU COME IN.
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU,
ERZA.
WHY DON'T WE PICK UP
WHERE WE LEFT OFF?
COME AND GET SOME.
- YOU'RE GONNA FIGHT AGAIN?
- MIRA.  YOU KNOW
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
WE NEVER DID
FINISH OUR MATCH,
DID WE?
- WHA--?!
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
- ( humming )
- THAT GIRL IS YOU?
- YEP.  SURPRISED?
- YEAH.  THIS DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE YOU AT ALL.
AND WAIT...
YOU SAID YOU WERE
PICKING A FIGHT WITH ERZA?
- ( giggles )
- I'M GONNA BURY YOU ALIVE!
- I'LL MAKE YOU
BEG FOR MERCY!
- IS THAT ARMOR
YOUR TRAINING BRA?
- LIKE SHOWING OFF
YOUR LOVE HANDLES?
- YOU UGLY PRUDE.
- YOU STUPID WENCH.
- THUNDER THIGHS.
- WAY TO KEEP IT CLASSY, GIRLS.
- OH, SURE.  SHE'S ALL MAD
WHEN WE GET IN A FIGHT,
BUT SHE CAN WRECK THE WHOLE
GUILD WHENEVER SHE WANTS?
- JUST WAIT.  ONE OF THESE DAYS
I'M GONNA GIVE THEM A BEATDOWN
THEY'RE NEVER GONNA FORGET.
- AW, GIVE ME A BREAK.
KEEP UP THAT TOUGH GUY ACT,
AND YOU'LL NEVER GET
THE GIRLS TO LIKE YOU.
- SHUT UP, LISANNA.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
- NOW DON'T BE MEAN.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO ASK
IF YOU NEEDED A HAND
RAISING THAT EGG?
- ( gasps )
YOU WANT TO HELP, REALLY?
- MM-HMM. I'VE NEVER
TRIED RAISING A DRAGON.
I BET IT'LL BE REAL FUN.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
"FUN"'S THE RIGHT WORD.
- SO HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO MAKE IT HATCH?
- I THINK YOU JUST
WARM IT UP.
- WHAT, FOR REAL?
LOOKS LIKE I'M
THE RIGHT MAN FOR THE JOB.
- NOT LIKE THAT, NATSU!
- ARE YOU STUPID?!
- JEEZ.
CAREFUL.  WE'RE TYING
TO HATCH THE EGG,
NOT POACH IT.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- SIT BACK AND LET
MY MAGIC HANDLE THIS.
TAKE OVER...
ANIMAL SOUL!
( giggles )
- WHOA, YOU'RE A BIRD!
- OH, I GET IT.
- WE'RE EXPERTS WHEN
IT COMES TO HATCHING EGGS.
- WOW, YOU'RE SO SMART.
- AW, ELFMAN,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- MY LITTLE SISTER'S PERFECTED
THE FULL-BODY TAKE OVER,
BUT I'M STILL HAVING
TROUBLE WITH IT.
I'M A SUCKY WIZARD.
- OH, I FORGOT YOU GUYS
USE THE SAME MAGIC.
- IF I WAS
AS STRONG AS HER,
I COULD TURN INTO A BIRD
AND LOOK FOR MY PARAKEET.
- PARAKEET?
- WE USED TO BE
THE BEST OF FRIENDS
TILL HE FLEW AWAY.
- THAT'S SO SAD.
- MAN, I WISH I HAD AN EGG
TO HATCH LIKE THEY DO.
- AWW.
SO THAT'S REALLY ELFMAN?
HE WAS SUCH
A CUTE LITTLE GUY.
- OH YEAH, HE HASN'T
CHANGED MUCH AT ALL.
- Narrator:
MAGNOLIA SOUTH GATE PARK.
- YOU'RE STARTING
TO MAKE ME NERVOUS.
- THE EGG WILL HATCH
IF WE SIT LIKE THIS?
- MM-HMM.
IT GETS KIND OF BORING THOUGH.
- ( rustling )
- WHOA, IT STARTED MOVING.
AAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
( gasps )
HUH.  LOOKS LIKE
IT CALMED DOWN.
HEY, MAYBE THE EGG'S
TRYING TO SAY SOMETHING
LIKE IT WANTS YOU
TO WARM IT UP INSTEAD.
- YEAH?
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- YEAH.
DOESN'T IT SEEM LIKE
IT'S HAPPY NOW?
- HEY EGG,
YOU WANT TO BE WITH ME?
- ( rustling )
- I THINK IT SAID YES.
- SEE, WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
- RIGHT AS ALWAYS.
- OOH, I HAVE AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE BUILD
THE EGG A LITTLE HOUSE?
- LIKE A SECRET BASE?
( grunts )
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS THAT THE AWESOMEST
HOUSE EVER OR WHAT?
- UH, YEAH.
PRETTY AWESOME.
- AAH!
I GUESS AWESOMENESS DOESN'T
COUNT FOR EVERYTHING, HUH?
- MY TURN NOW.
LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME.
- WHOA!  YOU'RE HUGE.
- PRETTY CUTE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
NOW HOLD ON
JUST A SEC.
- SO COOL.
ALL I'M GOOD FOR
IS BREAKING STUFF.
- TA-DA!
ALL DONE.
- WHOA.
NICE JOB, LISANNA.
- NOW LET'S CHECK OUT
THE INSIDE.
- I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE GONNA FIT.
WHOA.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
IT'S ACTUALLY
PRETTY ROOMY IN HERE.
- YEAH, ISN'T IT THOUGH?
ANYWAY,
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A SEAT?
- OH, SURE.
- ( giggles ) IT'S ALMOST LIKE
WE'RE A FAMILY NOW, HUH?
- HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
- WELL, YOU'VE GOT
A MOMMY AND A DADDY,
AND THE EGG IS LIKE
OUR LITTLE BABY
THAT HASN'T BEEN BORN YET.
- I GUESS THAT
DOESN'T SOUND SO BAD.
- ( giggles )
HOW ABOUT WE TRY
WARMING THE EGG TOGETHER?
- OKAY.
- IT'S WARM, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH.
- WHA-- IT MOVED AGAIN.
- OH, I HOPE
IT HATCHES SOON.
- YOU KIDDING ME?
A DRAGON'S EGG?
DON'T TELL ME YOU BELIEVE
IN ALL THAT GARBAGE?
- I DON'T KNOW. NATSU SAID
HE WAS RAISED BY A DRAGON,
SO WHY NOT?
- YEAH, LIKE I BUY THAT.
- GIVE THEM A BREAK,
THEY'RE KIDS.
LISANNA EVEN MADE
A LITTLE BITTY HOUSE
TO PROTECT THE EGG.
- YOU GUYS ARE LAME.
- THAT'S SO CUTE.
- AW, PUPPY LOVE.
- ( groans )
- ( both gasp )
- ( overlapping chatter )
- WHAT THE HECK'S
YOUR PROBLEM ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- CAN'T YOU JUST SULK AROUND
LIKE A NORMAL TEENAGER?
- I KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG
WHEN SHE DIDN'T
STOP BY THE GUILD.
SO SHE'S BEEN HANGING OUT
WITH NATSU, HAS SHE?
- YEAH.
- SHE CAN'T BE FRIENDS
WITH SOMEONE FROM
TEAM ERZA!
- SHE IS SERIOUSLY
P.O.'ED.
- TRY TO CHILL OUT.
JEEZ!
- OH, SO THIS IS WHERE
YOU FOUND THE EGG?
- UH-HUH.  IT FELL DOWN
FROM THE TREE WHEN I PUNCHED IT.
- I SEE.
- ( both gasp, scream )
- ( chuckles )
- Narrator: THIS MONSTER
IS A VICIOUS GORIAN
ALSO KNOWN AS
A FOREST VULCAN.
INCIDENTALLY,
IT'S FAVORITE FOOD IS...
- EGG.  GIVE IT TO ME, BOY.
- YEAH, FAT CHANCE.
YOU REALLY WANT TO
EAT SOMETHING?
HOW ABOUT MY FIST?!
- OH WOW.
THAT KIND OF TICKLES.
- YOU ASKED FOR IT.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
YOU'RE HURT,
LET ME HELP YOU.
- NO, JUST STAY BACK.
- BUT WHY?
- 'CAUSE I'M THE DAD,
AND I GOTTA PROTECT MY FAMILY.
- NATSU...
- BESIDES, I'M JUST
GETTING WARMED UP.
I'M THE SON OF A DRAGON,
YOU KNOW.
I WON'T LOSE TO A MONKEY!
- ( grunts )
- ( grunting )
- NATSU!
HIT HIM WITH YOUR MAGIC.
- IF THIS APE WANTS
TO FIGHT WITH HIS FISTS,
THEN THAT'S HOW
I'M GONNA BEAT HIM.
- I'D LOVE TO
SEE YOU TRY.
- YOU BETTER STOP YAPPING
AND START FIGHTING,
'CAUSE I'M GONNA
PAINT YOU WHITE
AND SEND YOU BACK
TO MOUNT HAKABE.
- ( shouts )
YOU MAKE ME MAD!
- BE CAREFUL!
- AAH!
- ( grunts )
- YOU DID IT,
YOU DID IT!
YOU SAVED THE DAY.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR FACE?!
THE EGG'S GONNA GET COLD.
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- HOLD ON.
WAIT HERE A SEC.
'KAY, COME IN.
- WHAT'S WITH HER?
- WELCOME BACK, DEAR.
- OH, WHAT?
- I SAID
"WELCOME BACK, DEAR."
- OH.  HI, HONEY.
I'M HOME?
- ( giggles )
- HM.
- GOOD THING
WE MADE IT HERE.
THE RAIN ISN'T STOPPING.
- ( stomach growls )
- UH, SORRY.
( groans )
- HEY, I WAS WONDERING.
YOU LIVE ALONE,
DON'T YOU?
- YEAH.
- THEN WHO COOKS
YOUR MEALS FOR YOU?
- I JUST EAT AT THE GUILD.
- SO DO YOU HAVE TO PAY?
- SURE.  WHY ELSE WOULD I
WORK ALL THE TIME?
- AW, THAT'S SAD.
- YOU THINK SO?
- YOU KNOW, I COULD
COOK DINNER FOR YOU
SOMETIME IF YOU'D LIKE?
- WHOA!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU COULD COOK.
- I'M NOT AS GOOD
AS MY SISTER THOUGH.
- WAIT, HOLD ON.
YOU'RE TELLING ME MIRA
ACTUALLY COOKS?
YOU MEAN LIKE FOOD, RIGHT?
NOT LITTLE CHILDREN?
DOES ELFMAN COOK TOO?
- YEAH.
OF COURSE HE DOES.
- ( Elfman humming )
COOK UP NICE FOR ME, OKAY?
- ACTUALLY THAT'S NOT
SO STRANGE AT ALL.
IT SUITS HIM PRETTY WELL.
NO!  I'M NOT
GIVING YOU THE EGG.
I BET IT'S IGNEEL'S KID.
I GOTTA LET IT HATCH.
DON'T YOU DARE TRY
TO FRY IT UP!
- DON'T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS!
NOW LISTEN,
I BUILT THIS HOUSE
SO WE COULD
RAISE THE EGG TOGETHER,
DIDN'T I?
I WANT IT TO HATCH
AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
- THEN WHY'D YOU
SCARE ME LIKE THAT, JERK?
AW, WHO'S MY LITTLE BUDDY?
YOU ARE, YOU ARE.
- EVEN IF YOU GET MAD
AND PICK FIGHTS ALL THE TIME,
YOU STILL HAVE
A SWEET SIDE, DON'T YOU?
JUST LIKE MIRA.
- HUH?
- IT'S BEEN FUN
PLAYING HOUSE WITH YOU.
MAYBE SOME DAY I COULD
BE YOUR REAL WIFE?
- WHAT--
WHAT GOT YOU
THINKING ABOUT THAT?
- I JUST NOTICED
HOW STRONG AND BRAVE YOU ARE,
AND YOU'RE GOOD
WITH KIDS TOO.
WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE?
- UH... YOU THINK SO?
- WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
SO EMBARRASSED ABOUT?
I WAS JUST
MAKING A JOKE.
- I KNOW THE WORD FOR YOU!
GRAMPS CALLS ME THAT:
NUVEJILE!
- JUVENILE?
JEEZ, YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
- ( groans )
NO FAIR!
WHY YOU GOTTA BE
SMARTER THAN ME?
- ( both gasp )
- WOW!
IT'S SO PRETTY.
IT'D BE NICE IF WE COULD
STAY LIKE THIS FOREVER,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- LOOK, IT'S MOVING AGAIN.
- UH-HUH.
- ( snoring )
- ( sighs )
- AAH!
THE EGG'S GONE!
- WHAT?!
- ALL RIGHT,
WHICH ONE OF YOU STOLE IT?
- WE DON'T WANT
YOUR DUMB EGG.
- I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
GRAY, YOUR CLOTHES.
- ( gasps )
- LAXUS, WAS IT YOU?
- YEAH RIGHT.
- OKAY, ERZA,
OUT WITH IT ALREADY.
- NOW NOW, LET'S NOT
JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS.
IT WASN'T ME.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, MIRA?
HAVE YOU SEEN THE EGG?
- NO. 'FRAID NOT.
YOU ATE IT,
DIDN'T YOU, PINKY?
JUST ADMIT IT.
- MIRA!
- ( gasps )
THAT'S IT.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- YEAH?
WELL, BRING IT ON.
I'LL SKIN YOU ALIVE, TWERP.
- Gray: NATSU, WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE PUNCHING, STUPID.
- Natsu: I'LL FIGHT YOU TOO!
- THEY'RE AT IT AGAIN.
- MAN, WHAT ARE WE GONNA
DO WITH THESE KIDS?
HATE TO THINK WHAT THE GUILD'S
GONNA BE LIKE IN A FEW YEARS.
- THEY ONLY FIGHT BECAUSE
THEY ACKNOWLEDGE
EACH OTHER'S STRENGTH
AND WHEN THEY SEE THEMSELVES
IN ONE ANOTHER,
IT MAKES THEM
STRIVE TO IMPROVE.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- YEAH, YOU WISH.
- WHY ARE YOU SO MEAN?
I JUST WANT MY EGG BACK.
- COME ON.
- AW, LOOK AT YOU CRYING.
HOW CUTE.
- I'M NOT CRYING!
- YOU HAVE TO QUIT
TEASING HIM ABOUT IT.
NOW, WOULD YOU
PLEASE STOP CRYING?
- I'LL MAKE YOU CRY!
- HURRY UP AND GIVE HIM
THE EGG BACK, ALL RIGHT?
- I TOLD YOU,
I AIN'T GOT IT.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU ATE IT,
PORKY.
- Erza: WHAT DID YOU CALL ME?!
- POOR EGG.
- Mirajane:
I SAW YOU EYEING THAT THING.
- ( crying )
- YOU KNOW, ELFMAN TOLD ME
HOW JEALOUS HE WAS
OF YOUR EGG
THE OTHER DAY.
- WHA--?!
- HE'S THE ONE WHO ATE IT?
- NO, HE'D NEVER DO THAT.
- HEY, SORRY, GUYS.
- IT WAS YOU ALL ALONG,
WASN'T IT?
- Lisanna: THE EGG.
- I DIDN'T MEAN
TO STEAL IT OR ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST YOU TOSS AND TURN
SO MUCH IN YOUR SLEEP,
I WAS AFRAID YOU WOULDN'T
KEEP THE EGG WARM ENOUGH.
- WAIT A SEC.
- SO IT'S OKAY?
- I'M NOT VERY GOOD WITH MAGIC,
BUT I STUCK CLOSE
TO IT ALL NIGHT,
AND KEPT IT WARM
WITH MY BODY HEAT.
- OH, I GET IT NOW.
- THANK YOU.
- THANKS A LOT.
YOU SURE ARE A REAL MAN.
- AND YOU BLAMED
EVERYTHING ON ME. TYPICAL.
- WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
THINGS ARE USUALLY YOUR FAULT.
- ( cracking )
- ( all gasp )
- HUH?
- NOW WHAT?
- IT'S HATCHING.
- ( meows )
- Both: WHOA, IT'S
A FREAKING CAT?
- ( both gasp )
- Natsu: IT HAS WINGS.
IS IT A BIRD?
- Lisanna:
NO, IT'S A CAT.
A BLUE CAT.
- ( chuckles )
- AYE!
- HE'S SO CUTE!
- All: I KNOW!
- ( chirps )
- IT'S A PARAKEET.
MY BEST FRIEND'S BACK!
OH!  HEY, BUDDY!
- YEAH RIGHT.
HIS PARAKEET WAS RED.
- DO YOU SEE THAT?
A MINUTE AGO,
EVERYONE HERE WAS ALL WORKED UP.
AND NOW THEY'RE HAPPY.
HE'S ALMOST LIKE A BLUEBIRD
OF HAPPINESS, ISN'T HE?
- HAPPINESS, HUH?
WELL, IN THAT CASE
I'LL NAME HIM HAPPY.
- AYE!
- HAPPY THE DRAGON!
- Mirajane: IT'S NOT A DRAGON.
- OH WELL.
I'LL PAINT IT AS ONE ANYWAY.
- I SEE.
THAT WAS A TOTALLY CUTE STORY.
I REALLY HATE TO SEE
THOSE TWO FIGHTING.
- THE CLOSER TWO PEOPLE ARE,
THE MORE THEY FIGHT.  IT'S FINE.
- HEY, MIRA.
THINK YOU COULD COME
HELP ME FOR A SEC?
- OF COURSE.
- NOW LET'S SEE...
THERE'S ERZA AND GRAY
AND MIRAJANE.
THAT'S LAXUS,
AND THIS GIRL MUST BE LISANNA.
THAT'S WEIRD.  IF SHE'S MIRA
AND ELFMAN'S SISTER,
HOW COME I HAVEN'T
MET HER YET?
I WONDER WHERE SHE IS.
- Lisanna: DON'T TELL ME
YOU TWO ARE FIGHTING AGAIN.
- Natsu: OH, HEY, LISANNA.
GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
- ( chuckles )
- HE ATE MY WHOLE FISH
AND DIDN'T EVEN ASK ME FIRST.
- WHENEVER I EAT ANY FISH
YOU SAY IT'S YOURS.
- JEEZ.  NATSU, YOU'RE THE DAD.
- HUH?
- SO YOU GOTTA TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOUR WIFE AND SON.
- THAT WAS LIKE
A MILLION YEARS AGO.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
- I-- NOTHING!
- IT'S NORMAL FOR FAMILIES
TO HAVE A FIGHT
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT
IS THAT YOU MAKE UP.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
HAPPY IS STILL OUR SON.
- I THINK LISANNA'S
GONE PSYCHO ON US.
- DON'T TALK LIKE THAT, MAN.
- Happy: ( Southern accent )
THEN SHOULD I TALK LIKE THIS?
- Natsu: YOU KNOW THAT'S
NOT WHAT I MEANT!
- Lisanna:
JUVENILE AS EVER, I SEE.
- Natsu:
STOP PICKING ON ME!
- ( Happy and Lisanna laugh )
- ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I GUESS I GOT NO CHOICE.
- THIS IS THE LAST STRAW.
I'M NEVER SPEAKING
TO NATSU AGAIN.
- HEY.
- I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
- THAT'S A REAL SHAME, 'CAUSE I
CAN'T EAT ALL THIS BY MYSELF.
- OH?
WHOA.
- SO, YOU HAPPY NOW?
- OF COURSE!
WHO ELSE WOULD I BE?
- ( Natsu chuckles )
- Lucy: IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
I WONDER IF THOSE TWO
HAVE MADE UP YET.
WELL, THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
I'D BETTER GO
CHECK ON THEM.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: PROFESSOR HAPPY'S
CLASS ABOUT "FAIRY TAIL."
TODAY, I'M GONNA TEACH YOU
THE SECRETS OF THE MAGIC GUILDS.
THERE ARE DIFFERENT KINDS
OF GUILDS ALL OVER THE WORLD.
THERE ARE EVEN SOME REALLY
SCARY ONES CALLED "DARK GUILDS."
BUT NO MATTER WHAT
GUILD THEY'RE FROM,
WIZARDS ALWAYS HAVE
THEIR GUILD'S MARK
SOMEWHERE ON THEIR BODY.
EACH ONE'S DIFFERENT.
SEE IF YOU CAN
SPOT THEM ALL.
BET YOU FEEL PRETTY SMART NOW,
DON'T YOU?
YAY!  DISMISSED!
AYE!
- THIS IS BAD.
THE GUILD HALL'S
BEEN TOTALLY WRECKED.
- I BET IT'S ERZA'S FAULT.
SHE PROBABLY GOT HUNGRY
AND WENT ON
ONE OF HER RAMPAGES.
- YEAH, THAT DOES
SOUND LIKE HER, HUH?
- AYE. WITH HER POWER,
IT'S A MIRACLE
THE BUILDING'S STILL STANDING.
- WELL, I'M IN
NO RUSH TO GO HOME.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
- Happy: SHE'S KIND OF LIKE
THE BEHIND THE SCENES LEADER
OF FAIRY TAIL, HUH?
- Natsu: YOU DON'T THINK
SHE'S GONNA TAKE OVER
THE GUILD SOME DAY, DO YOU?
- ( both murmur )