- HEY, GUYS!  READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT
TOO CLOSE TO THE TV.
- ( gasping )
- ( clamoring )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Simon: GRAY FULLBUSTER.
HE'S MORE POWERFUL THAN
MY INVESTIGATIONS
LED ME TO BELIEVE.
- Happy: YOU OKAY?
- WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
WE GOTTA RESCUE ERZA.
- Happy: NO.
YOU CAN'T GO DOWN, TOO.
- IS IT POSSIBLE HIS CONCERN
FOR HIS FRIENDS
INCREASED THE STRENGTH
OF HIS MAGIC?
- COME ON, YOU GOTTA
GET UP, NATSU.
- WHY'S EVERYTHING SPINNING?
- YOU COULDN'T HAVE CHOSEN
A BETTER GUILD, ERZA.
( Happy speaking )
- GENERATOR TOWERS IN PLACE.
- NO ERRORS DETECTED.
- ACQUIRING TARGET.
- SETTING SPATIAL COORDINATES.
- PREPARE TO REVERSE POLARITY.
- STAND BY FOR MAGIC FUSION.
- READYING SATELLITE
SQUARE PLACEMENT.
- COMMENCE MAGIC ELEMENT FUSION.
- WE'RE READING HEAVY DISTORTION
FROM THE MOUNTAIN
REGION'S WAVELENGTH.
- RE-CALCULATING SPATIAL
COORDINATES.
- I'M TOTALLY WIPED OUT.
I CAN'T EVEN MOVE A MUSCLE.
GUESS I OVERDID IT FIGHTING
THAT ROCKER FREAK.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE JUVIA'S DOWN
FOR THE COUNT, TOO.
- Millianna: WOW!
SOMEONE REALLY DID
A NUMBER ON THIS PLACE.
- HEY, YOU SEE WHAT I SEE, KID?
- I KNOW THAT VOICE.
- GOOD THING WE FOUND
THESE DAMES.
- WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I DON'T EVEN HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO TELL THESE GUYS WE'RE
NOT ENEMIES ANYMORE.
- MAGIC ENERGY LEVELS AT 60%.
- ETHERION FUSION IS UP TO 47%.
- PINPOINTING TARGET
IN 27 MINUTES.
- ELEMENTAL SUPERVISORS,
PLEASE HURRY!
- Org: SUCH A CRITICAL
DECISION TO MAKE.
AND WHILE THE CHAIRMAN IS ON
LEAVE DUE TO HIS AILING HEALTH,
IT IS OUR SOLEMN DUTY,
IN HIS ABSENCE,
WE NINE REMAINING COUNCIL
MEMBERS MUST DO WHATEVER IT
TAKES TO MAINTAIN ORDER.
- THERE'S NO NEED FOR YOU
TO WORRY, ORG.
I REALIZE WE'RE VIOLATING
INTERNATIONAL PROTOCOL
BY INITIATING
THIS MASSIVE ATTACK.
BUT WE'RE PROTECTED UNDER
CLAUSE 4 OF ARTICLE 27
OF THE NATIONAL
SECURITY DIRECTIVE.
- THE LEGALITY OF THIS
IS NOT MY CONCERN.
OUR DECISION TO FIRE
AN ETHERION BLAST
WILL PUT INNOCENT LIVES
AT RISK.
- IF ZEREF IS RESURRECTED,
MORE WILL BE AT RISK.
SADLY, AN EVIL FORCE OF THAT
MAGNITUDE CAN ONLY BE COUNTERED
BY SUCH EXTREME MEASURES.
- THE TIME HAS FINALLY
ARRIVED, MASTER SIEGRAIN.
- YES.
- AFTER ALL OF THESE YEARS,
YOUR DREAM WILL
BECOME A REALITY.
- LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
ARE YOU AFRAID?
- NO, NOT IN THE LEAST.
I TRUST YOU WHOLEHEARTEDLY
AND I HAVE COMPLETE FAITH
IN YOUR JUDGMENT.
- OF COURSE YOU'RE NOT.
WHY WOULD YOU BE?
YOUR LIFE ISN'T IN JEOPARDY.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- I MUST ADMIT.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
IF MY PLAN FAILS,
I WILL CEASE TO EXIST.
- WHAT?
- EVEN SO, I CONSIDER THE RISK
TO MY LIFE A SMALL PRICE TO PAY.
I'M SO CLOSE NOW.
MY DESTINY AWAITS.
- YES.
- TWENTY-FIVE MINUTES LEFT.
THE TIME HAS COME FOR US
TO SAY OUR FAREWELLS,
SIEGRAIN.
- HOW COULD YOU?!
YOU LIED TO ME, JELLAL.
YOU LIED TO ALL OF US.
I WON'T LET YOU GET AWAY
WITH IT.
- Erza: CALM DOWN, SHO.
- HE'S GOTTA PAY
FOR WHAT HE DID.
- YOU'RE GOING TO NEED MY HELP
TO FIGHT HIM.  RELEASE ME
FROM THIS CARD AT ONCE.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.  I'M SORRY,
BUT IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
YOU'RE SAFE IN THERE.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
- ( speaks Japanese )
I AM THE ONE THEY
CALL IKARUGA.
WHO MIGHT YOU BE?
- GET OUT OF MY WAY, LADY.
DON'T MAKE ME HURT YOU.
- DEAR ME,
WHY MUST I BE BURDENED
BY SUCH A BOORISH MAN?
- I WARNED YOU!
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
MY KATANA IS ABLE TO CUT
THROUGH ANYTHING
WITH EXTREME PRECISION.
- WELL, THAT SWORD
OF YOURS WON'T SCARE ME.
NO.  I-- I CAN'T MOVE.
- I'VE JUST SEVERED YOUR NERVES
WITHOUT CUTTING YOUR CLOTHING
OR FLESH.  DON'T CHALLENGE
MY MUGETSU STYLE.
- LET ME OUT OF HERE.
- I CAN'T.
- WELL, WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
I WONDERED WHERE YOU
WERE HIDING, ERZA.
- YOU'VE GOT TO RELEASE ME, SHO.
SHE'S TOO POWERFUL FOR YOU
TO TAKE ON BY YOURSELF.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
ALL THAT MATTERS IS YOU'RE SAFE.
I CAST A SHIELDING SPELL
ON THAT CARD.
SHE CAN'T HARM YOU
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
- IS THAT SO?
LET'S TEST THAT THEORY,
SHALL WE?
- YOUR SPELL WON'T HOLD UP
AGAINST HER.
THAT'S NO ORDINARY SWORD SHE'S
WIELDING. IT'S MAGICAL.
- YOU'RE SAFE.  I PROMISE.
TRUST ME.
SHE CAN CUT ACROSS
THE DIMENSIONAL RIFT?
SISTER.
- I SUSPECTED YOUR ATTACKS WOULD
WEAKEN SHO'S SEALING SPELL,
ALLOWING ME TO CUT RIGHT
THROUGH IT TO FREEDOM.
- A SWORD THAT CAN CUT THROUGH
DIMENSIONS IS AMAZING ENOUGH,
BUT HER ABILITY TO USE THAT
POWER TO HER ADVANTAGE
IS WHAT MAKES HER
EVEN MORE AMAZING.
- YOU SAID YOUR NAME'S IKARUGA.
WELL, I DIDN'T COME ALL
THIS WAY FOR YOU.  BE GONE.
- MY APOLOGIES,
BUT I THINK I'LL STAY.
- ( gasps )
- SISTER, NO.
- YOU SEEM SURPRISED.
A SKILLED WARRIOR LIKE YOU
SHOULD HAVE SEEN THAT COMING.
- ♪ CAN YOU FEEL ITS GAZE ♪
♪ FROM THE DEPTHS
OF THE NIGHT MIST? ♪
♪ THE MONONOKE ♪
- YOUR SINGLE-MINDED FOCUS
ON JELLAL
HAS RENDERED YOU
A FLEDGLING NOVICE.
COMPLETELY UNAWARE TO MY KATANA
FLASHING ABOUT YOU.
YES, THERE'S THE LOOK
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
- I'VE NEVER HER SEEN HER
LIKE THIS.
- YOU MAY BE SKILLED, BUT YOU
DON'T STAND A CHANCE AGAINST ME.
- YOU'RE MY ENEMY
AND I WILL DEFEAT YOU.
I ALWAYS DO.
- I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU TRY.
- HEAVEN'S WHEEL,
CIRCLE SWORD!
- MUGETSU STYLE.
- THAT WAS MY YASHA-SENKU.
- SHE CUT THROUGH THE SWORDS.
- ( screams )
- MUGETSU STYLE.
- PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
- KAHRUDAEN.
- AH, THE FLAME EMPRESS ARMOR.
IT'S HIGHLY RESISTANT
TO FLAME ATTACKS, IS IT NOT?
I'M IMPRESSED THAT YOU WERE
ABLE TO REQUIP SO QUICKLY.
HOW EMBARRASSING TO BE
SO INAPPROPRIATELY DRESSED
IN THAT YOUNG MAN'S PRESENCE.
I SUGGEST YOU ADORN YOURSELF
WITH THE MOST POWERFUL
ARMOR YOU POSSESS.
- WHAT A MONSTER.
- PURGATORY ARMOR
REQUIP COMPLETE.
YOU'LL REGRET YOUR ARROGANCE
WHEN I'M THROUGH WITH YOU.
NO ONE WHO'S SEEN THIS ARMOR
HAS LIVED TO TALK ABOUT IT.
- THIS IS THE MOST POWERFUL
ARMOR IN YOUR COLLECTION?
LET'S TEST ITS LIMITS.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- I'M SORRY, BUT YOU CAN'T
SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
YOU MADE A VALIANT EFFORT,
BUT THERE'S NO ARMOR
IN EXISTENCE THAT MY KATANA
CANNOT CUT THROUGH.
ADMIT YOUR DEFEAT.
- NO, THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
SHE CAN'T LOSE.
WHAT IS SHE THINKING?
SHE MUST BE OUT OF HER MIND.
- IS THIS SOME KIND OF JOKE?
WHY WOULD YOU TRADE OUT YOUR
ARMOR FOR AN OUTFIT MADE
OF REGULAR CLOTH?
- Sho: REQUIP!
- IS THIS PECULIAR CHOICE
OF DRESS DESIGNED TO MOCK ME?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HER LIKE THAT.
I'M SURE YOU'VE GOT ALL KINDS OF
HEAVY-DUTY ARMOR, RIGHT?
YOU'VE GOTTA STAY STRONG.
- I CAN'T DO THAT BECAUSE
I HAVE NEVER BEEN STRONG.
IT'S ALL A LIE.
I JUST PREFER TO BE ALONE
'CAUSE I GET NERVOUS
AROUND OTHER PEOPLE.
- Gray: WELL, YOU'RE ALONE NOW
SO WHY YOU CRYING?
- AS A CHILD, I WATCHED AS THOSE
CLOSE TO ME SUFFERED.
I LOST LOVED ONES BECAUSE
I DIDN'T HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO PROTECT THEM.
I TRIED TO BE STRONG.
I AM NOT CRYING.
BUT WHEN I WAS ALONE,
I COULDN'T HIDE MY EMOTIONS.
I DECIDED THAT IN ORDER
TO CONVINCE EVERYONE
THAT I WAS STRONG,
I WOULD HIDE MY HEART AWAY
INSIDE A SUIT OF ARMOR.
THERE, NO ONE COULD SEE
THAT IT WAS BROKEN.
I WEAR ARMOR
TO CONCEAL MY WEAKNESS
FROM THE REST
OF THE WORLD.
WITHOUT IT, I'VE BEEN
TOO AFRAID TO FIGHT.
- Ikaruga: WEAR IT OR NOT,
IT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE TO ME.
I'LL STRIKE YOU DOWN
JUST THE SAME.
- I THOUGHT MY ARMOR PROTECTED
ME, BUT IT DID MORE HARM
THAN GOOD.
IT SHIELDED ME FROM PAIN,
BUT IT KEPT ME DISTANCED
FROM OTHERS.
MY HEART WAS TOO GUARDED
TO CONNECT WITH ANYONE.
THAT IS, UNTIL I JOINED
FAIRY TAIL.
EVERYONE WAS SO WARM AND CARING
THAT MY COLD SHELL BEGAN
TO CRACK AND I BEGAN
TO FEEL EMOTIONS AGAIN.
- SISTER.
- I CAN'T RELY
ON MY ARMOR ANYMORE.
I KNOW I'M STRONG ENOUGH
TO DEFEAT YOU WITHOUT IT.  NOW!
- ( grunting )
- OUR BATTLE IS OVER.
MOST IMPRESSIVE.
- SISTER.
WHAT YOU DID WAS AMAZING.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I THINK SO.
- DEFEAT IS QUITE BITTER INDEED.
IN ALL OF MY YEARS,
I'VE ONLY KNOWN
THE SWEET TASTE OF VICTORY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
THAT YOU BEAT ME
BECAUSE YOU AND JELLAL
ARE BOTH DOOMED TO FAIL.
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- IN 15 MINUTES TIME...
♪ THE LIGHT OF JUSTICE ♪
♪ SHALL COME RAINING
FROM THE SKY ♪
♪ IT SHALL KILL US ALL ♪
WHAT A WRETCHED HAIKU.
- Erza: THE ETHERION BLAST.
SHO, GO FIND SIMON
AND MY FAIRY TAIL FRIENDS
AND GET EVERYONE AS FAR AWAY
FROM THE TOWER AS POSSIBLE.
- WHAT?  SISTER.
- I KNOW IT'S HARD,
BUT WILL YOU DO THIS FOR ME?
PLEASE.
- YEAH.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- I'M GOING TO SETTLE THINGS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- ( gasping )
WHAT THE--
- I WAS WONDERING WHEN YOU
WERE GONNA WAKE UP.
- THE LAST THING I REMEMBER WAS
FLYING AROUND IN CIRCLES--
- SERIOUSLY?
JUST THE MEMORY MAKES YOU SICK?
WELL, AFTER THAT YOU
WERE EATEN BY THE OWL.
LUCKILY, GRAY WAS ABLE
TO SAVE YOU.
- OH, GREAT.
- HE DEFEATED THE OWL,
BUT HE WAS BADLY WOUNDED
DURING THE FIGHT.
- WHERE'S ERZA?
- I DON'T REMEMBER
YOU BEING THIS HEAVY.
YOU REALLY NEED
TO LOSE SOME WEIGHT.
- SHUT UP, YOU DUMB CAT.
- YOUR FRIEND IS TAKING HIM
TO A SAFER PLACE.
- LOOK, IS THAT
THE SATELLITE SQUARE?
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
- LET'S PICK UP OUR SPEED.
- BUT WE'LL SAIL RIGHT
INTO THE FIORE NAVY.
- THAT'S BETTER THAN GETTING
CAUGHT IN THE ETHERION BLAST.
- AW, THERE GO ALL THE SHIPS.
- LOOK BELOW US.
- HUH?  COOL!
I FOUND A BOAT.
- NO, I SHOWED YOU
THE ONE WE CAME IN ON.
- NO WAY.
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
I LOST TO THAT OWL FREAK,
BUT GRAY WAS ABLE TO BEAT HIM?
- I WOULDN'T SAY THAT YOU LOST.
IT'S MORE LIKE YOU
WERE SWALLOWED.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT HAPPENED.
HE'S STILL GONNA HOLD THIS OVER
MY HEAD FOR AT LEAST
THE NEXT MONTH.
MAN, THIS SUCKS!
- YOU'RE MISSING THE POINT.
- I WON'T STAND FOR THIS.
I DEMAND A REMATCH.
BRING THAT BIRD BRAIN BACK AND
LET ME SHOW HIM WHAT I'VE GOT.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THAT
KIND OF NONSENSE RIGHT NOW.
- DON'T WANNA BE RUDE,
BUT DO I KNOW YOU?
- I'M SIMON. I WAS FRIENDS WITH
ERZA BACK WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
- OH, IN THAT CASE,
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
- ( wincing )
- ARE YOU OKAY, BIG GUY?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME. I'M
FINE.I JUST GOT WORD FROM WALLY.
- HE AND MILLIANNA
FOUND LUCY AND JUVIA,
BUT THEY'RE IN BAD SHAPE.
HE SAID IT LOOKED LIKE THEY TOOK
DOWN ONE OF THE TRINITY RAVEN
- ALL BY THEMSELVES.
- THE TWO OF 'EM?
- THEY HADN'T HEARD THAT
WE'RE NOT ENEMIES ANYMORE.
SO THEY WERE CONFUSED
WHEN I ASKED THEM
TO TAKE THE GIRLS
TO SAFETY.
- I GUESS THEY CALLED OFF
THE HIT ON THESE BROADS.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT SIMON SAYS
WE'RE FRIENDS NOW.
- YEAH, WELL IF WE'RE
SUCH GOOD FRIENDS,
WHY'D SHE TIE ME UP AND DRAG ME
ACROSS THE FLOOR LIKE THIS?
- Simon: SHO'S ALSO INFORMED ME
THAT THE LAST MEMBER
OF TRINITY RAVEN
HAS BEEN DEFEATED.
- I DIDN'T GET TO DO ANYTHING.
- NOW THEY'RE OUT OF THE
PICTURE,
THAT JUST LEAVES JELLAL.
ERZA'S GONE TO FIND HIM.
- BY HERSELF?
- SHE'S GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE
AND WHETHER WE LIKE IT OR NOT,
SHE'S WANTS TO DO IT
ON HER OWN.
I'M SURE YOU'RE AWARE SHE
AND JELLAL HAVE QUITE A HISTORY.
IT'S AS IF THEY'RE DESTINED
TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT HER
BECAUSE JELLAL'S STRONGER
THAN SHE KNOWS.
I BEG YOU.
YOU HAVE TO HELP HER FIGHT HIM.
- NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- ( sighs ) DON'T TELL ME
THE GAME'S OVER ALREADY.
- YOU FIND THAT MUCH PLEASURE IN
TOYING WITH THE LIVES OF OTHERS?
- BETWEEN THE MOMENT OF OUR
BIRTH AND THE TIME OF OUR DEATH,
THERE IS ONLY THAT GAME
OF EMOTIONS WE CALL LIFE.
WHAT COULD BE MORE DREARY THAN
SIMPLY EXISTING DAY AFTER DAY?
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
HASN'T IT?
- IT CERTAINLY HAS.
SHO AND THE OTHERS ARE NO LONGER
UNDER YOUR INFLUENCE.
- THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
NOW THAT THE TOWER OF HEAVEN
HAS BEEN COMPLETED,
I HAVE NO NEED FOR THEM.
- YOU DON'T SEEM TOO CONCERNED
IT'LL SOON BE DESTROYED.
- YOU MEAN BY THE ETHERION?
( laughs )
- YOU'RE SO CAREFREE, I CAN
ONLY ASSUME YOU WERE BLUFFING.
- NOT SO.  THE ETHERION
WILL RAIN DOWN ON US.
- I'M RELIEVED TO HEAR IT.
THAT MEANS I JUST NEED
TO KEEP YOU OCCUPIED
FOR THE NEXT TEN MINUTES,
AND THIS NIGHTMARE
WILL BE OVER AT LAST.
NO.
WHEN THE BEAM STRIKES,
YOUR LIFE WILL BE SACRIFICED
TO ZEREF.
THIS HAS ALWAYS BEEN CERTAIN.
YOU CANNOT AVOID FATE, ERZA.
THIS IS YOUR DESTINY.
- Gray: COME ON, YOU GUYS.
TURN THIS BOAT AROUND RIGHT NOW.
- THAT AIN'T HAPPENING,
SO CLOSE YOUR HEAD.
- ERZA SAID TO GET AS FAR AWAY
FROM THE TOWER AS WE CAN.
- BUT NOW SHE AND NATSU HAVE NO
WAY TO LEAVE.  THEY'RE STUCK.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
THEY'RE GONNA BE FINE.
I KNOW IT.
- HE CAN'T DO IT ALONE.
NATSU NEEDS ME THERE
TO BACK HIM UP.
- FORGET ABOUT IT.
SIMON'S WITH HIM
SO I'M SURE IT'LL
WORK OUT JUST DANDY.
WELL, IT'S NOT GONNA BE "DANDY"
IF THEY END UP DEAD.
- YEAH, WELL YOU DON'T HAVE TO
YELL LIKE THAT.
- WE SHOULDN'T BE
FIGHTING YOU GUYS.
- SHUT YOUR TRAP AND TAKE ME
BACK TO THE SHORE RIGHT NOW.
I GOTTA GO BACK FOR HER.
- I'M WITH HIM. TURN
THE BOAT AROUND.
- I TOLD YA,
THAT AIN'T HAPPENING!
- JUST SHUT UP!
QUIT YELLING AT EACH OTHER
AND JUST TRY TO GET ALONG.
I WANNA GO BACK FOR THEM TOO,
BUT WE CAN'T
'CAUSE THE ETHERION'S GONNA
BLAST THAT PLACE ANY MINUTE NOW.
NATSU'S GONNA SAVE ERZA.
AND THEY'RE GONNA MAKE IT
OUT OF THERE ALIVE.
SIMON TOLD ME THAT'S
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN.
HE SAID ONCE NATSU'S TRUE POWER
AWAKENS WITHIN HIM,
HE'S GONNA BE UNSTOPPABLE.
( sobbing )
NOT EVEN JELLAL WILL BE ABLE
TO BEAT HIM.
- ( crying )
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU CLAIM TO BE ERZA'S FRIEND,
BUT YOU REFUSE TO HELP HER?
- THIS IS HER FIGHT.
SHE WANTS TO HANDLE IT
ON HER OWN.
SHE'D NEVER FORGIVE ME
IF I BUTTED IN
ON THE ACTION LIKE THAT.
- THERE'S NO WAY THAT SHE COULD
EVER WIN AGAINST JELLAL.
- WHAT?  SHE'S STRONGER
THAN YOU GIVE HER CREDIT FOR,
SO WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
- YOU'VE GOT IT WRONG.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT I DOUBT
THE POWER OF HER MAGIC.
DESPITE EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED,
I KNOW ERZA STILL WANTS
TO TRY TO SAVE JELLAL.
I HAVE NO DOUBT IN MY MIND.
IN HER HEART,
SHE COULD NEVER TRULY HATE
THE BOY SHE REMEMBERS
FROM CHILDHOOD.
JELLAL IS VICIOUSLY CUNNING.
HE KNOWS EXACTLY HOW
TO MANIPULATE HER FEELINGS
TO HIS ADVANTAGE.
AND THAT'S NOT THE ONLY THING
WORKING AGAINST HER.
AS YOU KNOW, THE MAGIC
COUNCIL IS PREPARING
TO FIRE AN ETHERION BLAST.
WHEN THAT HAPPENS, THE TOWER
AND ANYONE INSIDE IT
WILL BE WIPED OUT.
IF WHAT SHO TOLD ME IS CORRECT,
WE ONLY HAVE TEN MINUTES.
- WHAT?
- SHE ORDERED EVERYONE ELSE
TO LEAVE THE TOWER
AND WENT TO FACE HIM ALONE.
IF YOU KNOW HER
AS WELL AS YOU SAY,
THEN YOU KNOW WHAT SHE'S UP TO.
SHE'S GIVING UP HER LIFE
AND WHEN THE BLAST COMES,
IT WILL TAKE THEM
BOTH DOWN TOGETHER.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID THAT
TO BEGIN WITH.
TELL ME WHERE I CAN FIND ERZA.
- Jellal: THERE ARE ONLY
SEVEN MINUTES LEFT.
WHEN THE ETHERION
STRIKES THE TOWER,
WE'LL TAKE OUR FINAL BREATHS.
WHY DON'T WE SIMPLY ENJOY
THESE LAST MOMENTS TOGETHER?
- YOU SHOULD KNOW I'VE CAST OFF
ALL MY FEARS.
EVEN OF MY OWN DEATH.
I'LL RELISH IN IT BECAUSE I'LL
BE TAKING YOU DOWN WITH ME.
- OH, REALLY?
IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
WELL, WE'LL JUST SEE
ABOUT THAT.
- YOU'D DESTROY THE VERY THING
YOU WORKED SO HARD TO COMPLETE?
WHAT'S THE POINT?
- WHY SHOULD I CARE ABOUT
A PILLAR OR TWO?
AFTER ALL, THEY'RE NOTHING
BUT DECORATIONS.
- MAYBE SO BUT THE REASON
THEY'RE HERE
IS BECAUSE THE OTHERS SPENT
ALL THOSE YEARS
BUILDING THEM FOR YOU.
- HOW IS IT YOU MANAGE TO FIND
FAULT IN EVERYTHING I SAY?
I NEVER FORCED THEM TO WORK.
THEY CHOSE TO.
THEY KNEW HOW IMPORTANT
THE TOWER WAS TO ME.
AND NOW, AT LONG LAST,
IT'S BEEN COMPLETED.
- ( gasps )
WHILE IT'S EVIDENT YOU'VE HONED
YOUR SKILLS OVER THE YEARS,
YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR ME.
- ( sobbing )
- Gray: YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT
'CAUSE THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU
AT ALL.
WE WANNA STAY HERE
AND HELP YOU OUT.
MASTER TAUGHT US THAT EVEN
THE STRONGEST WARRIORS
NEED A LITTLE BACKUP EVERY
ONCE IN A WHILE.
- Lucy:
AND NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
WE'RE ALWAYS GONNA
HAVE YOUR BACK.
- Happy: AYE!
WE'RE THE STRONGEST TEAM.
- Simon: I'VE ALWAYS BELIEVED
IN YOU, ERZA.
AND THERE'S NOTHING
THAT COULD CHANGE THAT.
- Sho: SISTER.
- Erza: I'LL MISS THEM.
- I WANT A REMATCH WHEN WE GET
BACK TO FAIRY TAIL.
- I TOLD YOU.  I'VE CAST OFF
ALL MY FEARS, INCLUDING YOU.
( shouts )
- THIS IS NOT THE WEAK GIRL
I REMEMBER.
( grunts )
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, HAPPY.  JUST WONDERING,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THIS ETHERION THINGY THAT
EVERYONE'S FREAKING OUT ABOUT?
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YOU'RE A WIZARD
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT IS?
IT'S AN EXTREMELY POWERFUL
WEAPON CONTROLLED
BY THE MAGIC COUNCIL THAT CAN
DISINTEGRATE EVERYTHING
IN ITS PATH.
- WOW!
THEN I GUESS IT WOULD BE REALLY
BAD IF IT HIT US, HUH?
WE CAN'T WASTE ANY MORE TIME
SITTING AROUND HERE.
WE GOTTA FIND ERZA.
- NATSU, YOU BETTER GET
WITH THE PROGRAM PRETTY SOON,
OR WE WON'T HAVE A PRAYER.