- I'M GONNA CLAIM
THE TITLE
OF S-CLASS WIZARD
AND I'LL HAVE A BALL
KICKING ERZA'S TEETH IN
WHILE I DO IT.
I THINK I SEE SOMEBODY.
- IS IT ERZA?
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- NO FRICKIN' WAY!
- SORRY, DEAD END.
LUCK JUST
AIN'T ON YOUR SIDE.
- WE'RE DEAD.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: PREVIOUSLY
ON "FAIRY TAIL..."
- ( bells ring )
- Townspeople: WHOA.
( chattering )
- ( ringing continues )
- WHAT'S UP?
- Both: SOUNDS LIKE BELLS.
- I BET I KNOW WHY
THEY'RE RINGING. - AYE.
- OLD GILDARTS
IS COMING BACK HOME.
- OH, YEAH!
- WELL, IT'S GOOD HE'S BACK,
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY EVERYONE'S
GOING TOTALLY NUTS.
- LOOK HOW HAPPY
THEY ALL ARE.
- Carla: THEY'RE CERTAINLY
MORE OUT OF CONTROL THAN USUAL.
- IT'S ONLY NATURAL
EVERYONE'S EXCITED.
HE'S BEEN GONE
QUITE A WHILE.
THREE YEARS IN FACT.
- Lucy: WHOA, NO WAY!
YOU MODIFIED THE TOWN
JUST 'CAUSE HE'S CLUMSY?!
- Wendy: HE SOUNDS AMAZING!
- Carla: YES, AMAZINGLY STUPID.
- Natsu: HERE HE COMES.
- Happy: AYE.
- COME ON, YOU OLD GEEZER.
LET'S THROW DOWN.
- THAT'S NO WAY
TO TREAT A MAN.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU!
NOW LET'S PARTY!
UGH! OY-OY-OY, AH!
( weak chuckles )
OH, YEAH.
HE STILL SO AWESOME.
- ( clears throat ) IN
ACCORDANCE WITH
THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD'S
TIME-HONORED TRADITION,
I WILL NOW ANNOUNCE
THIS YEAR'S ENTRANCE
FOR THE S-CLASS
WIZARD-PROMOTION TRIAL.
THE STRENGTH THAT
YOU POSSESS INSIDE,
YOUR CHARACTER,
AND YOUR HEARTS,
THESE ARE WHAT I CONSIDERED
WHILE MAKING MY SELECTION.
AND I HAVE CHOSEN
EIGHT PARTICIPANTS.
NATSU DRAGNEEL.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
- GRAY FULLBUSTER.
- IT'S FINALLY MY TIME
TO MOVE UP.
- JUVIA LOXAR.
- REALLY?
THE MASTER CHOSE ME?
- ELFMAN.
- S-CLASS DESERVES
A REAL MAN LIKE ME.
- CANA ALBERONA.
FRIED JUSTINE.
LEVY MCGARDEN.
AND MEST GRYDER.
- ( Happy speaking )
- Narrator:
WE JOIN OUR HEROES HERE
ON TENROU ISLAND
FOR THE FIRST ROUND
OF THE S-CLASS
WIZARD-PROMOTION TRIAL
IS CURRENTLY UNDERWAY.
THIS IS ONE OF
THE EIGHT PATHS
CONTESTANTS HAD
TO CHOOSE FROM.
ROUTE "D."
- ( rumbling )
- ( girls screaming )
- SO STRONG.  HAS SHE
ALWAYS BEEN THIS POWERFUL?
- PRETTY MUCH.
- Erza: YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT, JUVIA.
YOU'LL NEVER BECOME
AN S-CLASS WIZARD AT THIS RATE.
- Lisanna:
HER SEA EMPRESS ARMOR.
YOUR ATTACKS AREN'T GONNA
HAVE ANY EFFECT ON HER NOW.
- ( gasping )
I CAN DO THIS.
I WILL DEFEAT YOU.
WATER SLICER!
SHE DEFLECTED MY ATTACK
LIKE IT WAS NOTHING.
- I'VE GOT YOU NOW, ERZA.
- ( both gasp )
- ( thudding )
- ( screams )
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
TAKE OVER!
YOU'VE IMPROVED A LOT.
I'M QUITE IMPRESSED.
BUT YOU CAN STILL USE
SOME WORK ON YOUR TIMING
AS WELL AS
THE FORMS YOU CHOOSE.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH A BUNNY?
- THAT'S IT.
ERZA'S VULNERABLE
WHEN SHE COUNTERS
LISANNA'S ATTACKS.
IF I STRIKE AT
THE RIGHT MOMENT,
I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO TAKE HER DOWN.
IT'S MY ONLY HOPE.
- FINE, IS THIS BETTER?
( screams )
- WATER WHIP!
I TOLD YOU
I'D DEFEAT YOU!
- ( screams )
- ( ragged scream )
- THAT HURT.
- I'M DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU, JUVIA.
YOU'VE GOT TO
BE MORE CREATIVE.
ATTACKING YOUR OPPONENT WHILE
THEY'RE FIGHTING YOUR TEAMMATE
IS THE MOST OBVIOUS
TWO-ON-ONE STRATEGY
YOU COULD HAVE CHOSEN.
NOT ONLY THAT,
BUT AS YOU'VE WITNESSED,
IT'S AN ATTEMPT
THAT'S EASILY THWARTED.
I EXPECTED MUCH MORE.
WHEN WE FIRST MET
AT THE TOWER OF HEAVEN,
YOU WERE FULL OF
DETERMINATION AND SPIRIT.
THERE WAS A FIRE
IN YOUR EYES.
WHERE IS THAT FIRE NOW?
TELL ME!
- ( screams )
- ( screams, gasps )
- ( screams echo )
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
LUCY AND CANA TAKE A BREAK
AFTER SUCCESSFULLY
CLEARING THE FIRST ROUND.
- ( Lucy sighs in pleasure )
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT I NEEDED.
FEELS GREAT.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
GET OVERHEATED SO EASILY.
- IT'S NOT LIKE
I CAN HELP IT
WHEN IT'S SO
FREAKIN' HOT OUT HERE.
- ( sighs )
HEY, WE SHOULD GET GOING.
- CAN WE STAY
A LITTLE LONGER?
WE'RE NOT IN A RUSH
OR ANYTHING.
- WHAT'S WITH THIS
"I DON'T GIVE A CRAP" ATTITUDE?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- I'M WORRIED NATSU'S STUPIDITY
MIGHT BE RUBBING OFF ON YOU.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I'M JUST BEING HARDHEADED
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO GET OUT RIGHT NOW.
COME ON, CANA.
WE'RE DRENCHED IN SWEAT.
AND THIS IS OUR CHANCE
TO WASH IT AWAY.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
SOMEWHERE ALONG ROUTE "A..."
- GREAT.
WE'RE SO SCREWED.
- OF ALL THE PEOPLE
TO RUN INTO.
- ( growling )
- ( both whimper )
- ( deep demonic pitch )
I'M NOT HOLDING BACK
JUST CAUSE YOU'RE
MY LITTLE BROTHER.
UNDERSTOOD?
- ( whimpers )
- HELLO! I'M HERE.
YOU GOT TO FIGHT ME TOO,
YOU KNOW?
- ( gasping )
SO THIS IS THE POWER...
OF AN S-CLASS WIZARD?
- I SHOULD WARN YOU.
I'VE NEVER BEEN GOOD AT
HOLDING BACK IN A FIGHT.
SO THIS'LL BE QUICK.
- I'M FIRED UP NOW.
UH, HAPPY, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING?
- FIGURED WE MIGHT AS WELL
HEAD HOME.
- HAVE SOME FAITH IN ME,
LITTLE BUDDY.
IF YOU REALLY
THINK ABOUT IT,
GILDARTS SHOULD
BE SCARED OF ME.
I'M GONNA KICK HIS BUTT
AND I WON'T LET UP
UNTIL I HEAR HIM SAY "MERCY."
- FINE, MERCY.
- YOU CAN'T SAY THAT YET!
I HAVEN'T EVEN
LAID A HAND ON YOU.
I'M COMING FOR YOU, GILDARTS!
I GOT A HECK OF A LOT STRONGER
OVER THE LAST THREE YEARS.
AND I CAN'T WAIT
TO SHOW YOU.
- NO, WAIT ONE MINUTE, NATSU.
- ( growling )
- TRY TO CALM DOWN, WOULD YOU?
I'M NOT READY TO BEGIN
OUR FIGHT JUST YET.
STAY BACK.
- YOU SHOULDN'T RUSH
AT HIM LIKE THAT, NATSU.
HE CAN PULVERIZE
HIS OPPONENTS.
- ( grunts )
( Natsu screams )
- I WARNED YOU.
- GEEZ, KID, HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE I TOLD YOU?
HOLDING BACK IN BATTLE
ISN'T EXACTLY MY THING.
- OH, NO.
HOW COULD YOU?
POOR GUY'S BEEN BLOWN
TO SMITHEREENS.
- Natsu: YEAH, RIGHT!
HE WISHES!
- WHOA, HE SHATTERED THE GROUND
TO CUSHION THE BLOW.
- THERE'S MORE WHERE
THAT CAME FROM!
( grunting )
( groaning )
YEARGH!
- HE'S BEATING HIM SILLY!
NATSU'S SERIOUS.
YOU CAN TELL BY THE LOOK
ON HIS FACE.
- ( screams )
( chuckles )
- Happy: BUT HE'S STILL SMILING.
FIRE DRAGON...
ROAR!
- YEAH, YOU HAVE
GOTTEN STRONGER.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, NATSU...
THE DRAGON'S SON.
- ( gasping )
( screams )
- ( gasps )
- UH-OH.
- ( groans )
- NATSU?
- CRAP, I OVERDID IT.
- YOU JERK.
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
THIS WAS JUST
SUPPOSED TO BE A TEST.
YOU KILLED HIM!
- RELAX.
I SERIOUSLY DOUBT
HE'S DEAD.
IT WASN'T THAT
KIND OF MAGIC.
LOOK UP.
- ( Natsus groaning )
- DISASSEMBLY MAGIC
BREAKS ITS TARGET DOWN
INTO LITTLE PIECES.
- THERE'S A TON OF NATSUS!
- ( chattering )
- AAH!
- DON'T WORRY. HE'LL GO
BACK TO NORMAL IN A BIT.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS MEANS
YOUR TEST IS OVER, NATSU.
SORRY, BUT I CAN'T PASS YOU.
- Natsus: NOT SO FAST,
YOU OLD GEEZER!
YOU GOT ANOTHER THING COMING
IF YOU THINK
I'M GONNA GIVE UP
THAT EASILY.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME
JUST 'CAUSE I'M TINY.
I'LL CHAR YOUR FACE OFF!
( chatter )
- PLEASE STOP!
- HEY, I JUST CAME UP
WITH A BRILLIANT IDEA.
I DID TOO.  WE SHOULD
ALL GANG UP GILDARTS!
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY?
GREAT MINDS THINK ALIKE.
YOU THINK YOU CAN BEAT
AN ARMY OF NATSUS?!
( high-pitch battle cries )
- ( laughing )
WELL, THIS IS A FIRST.
I'VE NEVER BEEN CHALLENGED
BY A MINI ARMY BEFORE.
- ( water laps )
- ( bones crack )
OH, MAN.
IT FEELS GOOD
TO BE HOME.
- HERE I COME!
- AYE, SIR!
- FIRE DRAGON
SWORD HORN!
- NEVER SAW IT COMING.
- OH, IT'S JUST YOU.
- OF COURSE!
WANT SOME MORE OR ARE
YOU GONNA SAY MERCY?
- SAY IT.
- OH, COME ON, KID.
I JUST GOT BACK INTO TOWN.
DON'T YOU THINK I DESERVE
SOME TIME TO RELAX?
- NO WAY! I'M ABOUT TO BEAT
YOUR BRAINS OUT RIGHT NOW!
- ARE YOU SCARED?
- FIRE DRAGON...
IRON FIST!
- AH! NATSU!
- ( chuckles )
- MAN, THAT HURTS.
I SWEAR, THAT GUY'S GOT TO BE
SOME KIND OF MONSTER.
- YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
- DON'T YOU WORRY!
I'M NOT LETTING THAT JERK
BEAT ME AGAIN!
- AYE!
- Young Natsu: GILDARTS!
I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU!
- YO. - HEY,
HOW'S YOUR DAY GOING, NATSU?
- ( screams, grunts )
- Both: INSTANT K.O.
- AT LEAST HAVE
THE DECENCY TO SAY HELLO
WHEN SOMEONE GREETS YOU.
WHERE'RE YOUR MANNERS, KID?
- SORRY.  HELLO.
- LOOKS LIKE
HE'S AT IT AGAIN.
YOU'D THINK HE WOULD'VE
LEARNED BY NOW.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
THAT BONEHEAD'LL NEVER LEARN.
- MIRA, HE MAY NOT BE
THE SHARPEST TOOL IN THE SHED,
BUT I THINK HIS COURAGE
IS COMMENDABLE.
- WOW, LOOK AT YOU PULLING
OUT THE BIG WORDS TODAY.
YOU'RE SO LAME.
YOU PROBABLY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT COMMENDABLE MEANS.
- IF YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING TO SAY,
THEN GO AHEAD AND SAY IT,
YOU SIMPLEMINDED STRUMPET!
- QUIT TRYING TO ACT LIKE
YOU'RE SO MUCH BETTER ME
OR I'M GONNA KNOCK
YOUR TEETH IN, GOT IT?!
- KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
AFTER HELLO?!
- OOH! I KNOW!
- FIRE DRAGON
TALON TO THE HEAD!
- CHEAP SHOT.
- ( laughs )
- Both: SCARY!
- ( screams )
- YOU'RE ON, NATSU.
LET'S TAKE THIS OUTSIDE.
- THAT WORKS.
HE'S ALREADY OUTSIDE.
- I THINK WE SHOULD
CALL A TRUCE THIS ONCE.
THEIR FIGHT'S GONNA BE
WAY MORE BRUTAL THAN OURS.
- GOOD POINT,
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
- EVERYBODY'S SURE GETTING THEIR
PANTIES IN A WAD OVER THIS.
- Young Elfman: SO YOU'RE
NOT GONNA GO WATCH WITH THEM?
- I NEVER SAID THAT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, CANA?
ARE YOU GONNA GO
WATCH THE FIGHT?
- ME? UH...
NO, I'LL STAY HERE.
- ( unsure ) OKAY.
- ( screaming )
( grunting )
- ( thumping )
- ( groaning )
- YOU HAVEN'T GOTTEN
A SINGLE HIT IN YET, NATSU.
- SHUT UP.
I KNOW.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER? DON'T
TELL ME THAT'S ALL YOU GOT?
- LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, GILDARTS.
- YEAH?
- I KNOW YOU'RE POWERFUL.
YOU'RE THE STRONGEST GUY
IN THE WHOLE GUILD.
- YOU'RE LOOKING
PRETTY WOBBLY THERE.
- Young Natsu:
THAT'S WHY I GOT TO BEAT YOU.
IT'LL HAPPEN SOMEDAY.
- ( thudding )
- YOU KNOW IT'S
KIND OF HARD TO TAKE
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING SERIOUSLY
WHEN YOU JUST KEEL OVER
LIKE THAT, NATSU.
- WE'RE GONNA FIGHT.
IT'LL HAPPEN...
SOMEDAY.
- OKAY, BUT
I'M WARNING YOU NOW,
I WON'T HOLD BACK...
OR LOSE.
-  ( Natsus growl )
READY OR NOT,
HERE I COME!
- IT'S A HOARD
OF MINI NATSUS!
- HERE WE GO AGAIN.
- ( battle cries )
( screaming )
( groans, chatter )
( battle screams )
HA!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
FIRE DRAGON ROAR!
- THEY'RE SO CREEPY.
- YOU'RE ANNOYING ME.
- YOU THOUGHT THIS WAS
GONNA BE EASY, DIDN'T YOU?
- TIME TO GO BACK
TO NORMAL, NATSU.
- ( high-pitched screams )
( chuckles )
HERE I COME!
DRAGON SLAYER SECRET ART!
- UH-OH!
- FLAME LOTUS:
EXPLODING FLAME BLADE!
- DID HE GET HIM?
- ( pants )
( gasps )
- THAT'S CRAZY.
YOU ATTACKED AT FULL POWER
AND HE DIDN'T
EVEN FLINCH.
LOOKS LIKE IT
DIDN'T FAZE HIM AT ALL.
- YEAH, IT DID.
YOU GOT TO TAKE
A CLOSER LOOK, HAPPY.
THE OLD MAN TRIED
TO STAND FIRM,
BUT MY BLAST MOVED HIM
BACK A FEW FEET.
( laughs )
NOT TO MENTION
HIS CAPE'S ALL MESSED UP.
- DID HE REALLY MOVE HIM?
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
HE'S RIGHT.
GILDARTS DIDN'T
TAKE A SINGLE STEP.
( screams )
WAIT, THAT'S BAD NEWS FOR NATSU
'CAUSE GILDARTS
BARELY MOVED
AND HE STILL BEAT HIM.
- ( chuckles )
( weakly groans )
- YOU'RE WOBBLING LIKE
THE LAST TIME YOU GUYS FOUGHT.
- I'VE GOT THIS.
- YEAH, SURE YOU DO.
NOT!
- VERY IMPRESSIVE WORK, NATSU.
THIS GAVE ME A GOOD FEEL
FOR YOUR SKILL LEVEL.
YOU MAY NOT HAVE
DEFEATED ME IN BATTLE,
BUT AS YOUR EXAMINER,
I THINK YOU DESERVE
TO MOVE ON TO
THE NEXT ROUND.
- THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GIVING UP NOW.
I'LL BEAT YOU, GILDARTS!
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF MOVING UP TO S-CLASS
IF I CAN'T EVEN DO THAT?!
- I HAD A FEELING
YOU WERE GONNA SAY THAT.
- ( rumbling )
- ( wind rushes )
- BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'LL WANT
TO KEEP THIS UP
ONCE I'VE FINALLY
UNLEASHED MY FULL POWER.
- ( gasps )
- THERE'S SOME KIND OF PRESSURE
BUILDING UP IN HERE.
- IN ORDER TO WALK
THE PATH OF MAGIC
AND EVENTUALLY
REACH ITS PEAK,
THERE IS ONE THING
YOU STILL LACK.
- ( wind rushes faster )
- LET ME SHOW YOU.
- ( gasping )
- WHOA, WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S MAGIC POWER.
AN INCREDIBLE AMOUNT.
- ( frightened gasping )
- HMM.
- ( whimpers )
( harsh breathing )
( growls )
( screams )
( yelps )
( panting )
( growls )
( whimpers )
( frightened gasps )
( shaky gasps )
I...
ACCEPT DEFEAT.
- NATSU.
- A WISE CHOICE.
I APPLAUD ANYONE
WHO HAS THE COURAGE
TO STAND UP AND
FACE THEIR ENEMIES.
HOWEVER, THE WIZARDS
WHO ARE THE MOST COURAGEOUS
ARE THOSE EXCEPTIONAL FEW
WHO KNOW WHEN
TO STAND DOWN.
REMEMBER, NATSU.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH FEELING FEAR.
AFTER ALL, HOW ELSE WOULD WE
COME TO KNOW
OUR OWN WEAKNESSES?
YOU NEED TO KNOW THEM
IN ORDER TO BECOME A STRONGER
AND GENTLER PERSON,
A NECESSITY FOR THOSE
WHO WANT TO BE S-CLASS.
NOW THAT I'VE SHARED
THIS KNOWLEDGE WITH YOU...
YOU PASS, KID.
- ( gasps )
BUT I DIDN'T BEAT YOU.
- DON'T ARGUE WITH ME.
I'M YOUR EXAMINER
AND I SAY YOU'VE PASSED.
YOU'VE MADE IT THROUGH
THE FIRST ROUND,
BUT THIS IS JUST
THE BEGINNING.
YOU KNOW HOW
MASTER CAN BE.
I'M SURE THIS WAS
NOTHING COMPARED
TO WHAT HE'S GOT
IN STORE FOR YOU.
HAVE CONFIDENCE IN YOURSELF.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
NOW, THAT WE'VE FINISHED
UP YOUR TEST,
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING
AS A FRIEND.
POSSESSING POWERFUL MAGIC
ISN'T THE BE-ALL END-ALL.
ONE THING I CAN
TRULY APPRECIATE
IS YOUR HUNGER TO WIN,
YOUR BURNING DESIRE
FOR VICTORY.
I SAY THAT
'CAUSE I HAVE IT TOO.
LIKE YOU,
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE.
I'LL TAKE YOU ON
AGAIN ANYTIME.
NOW GO BECOME
AN S-CLASS WIZARD.
YOU HEAR ME?
- ( cries )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Happy: YOU KNOW,
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
I CAN'T REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I SAW THAT MEST GUY.
WHAT'S HIS DEAL AGAIN? - THEY
SAY HE WAS MYSTOGAN'S PUPIL.
SO, I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS
THEY TRAVELLED AROUND TOGETHER.
- HOW COME HE DIDN'T SHOW UP
DURING THE EDOLAS STUFF?
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
HE DIDN'T POP UP ONCE.
WAIT, I'M NOT EVEN SURE
I'VE MET HIM BEFORE.
- OF COURSE YOU HAVE.
HE'S A MEMBER OF OUR GUILD.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
THAT ONE TIME?
HE DID THAT THING.  UH...
- MAYBE HE USES
SOME KIND OF MAGIC
THAT MAKES US OVERLOOK HIM.
- THAT MUST BE IT.