Where is Zeref?
I need to find Zeref right now.
[NATSU]
He's there.
Natsu.
It's you.
[NATSU]
Gray.
[GRAY]
Natsu.
Move, Gray.
All this time,
you've been E.N.D.
Get out of my way!
I know it's you!
[NATSU]
Zeref must die.
I must kill Zeref.
I can't get through to you.
Are you still in there?
[NATSU]
Don't. Don't interfere.
I have to kill Zeref!
[INVEL] The demons of
the Books of Zeref.
They're essentially tools
His Majesty created
to bring about his own death.
He views his immortality
as a curse.
So to end his suffering,
he developed a demon
powerful enough to kill him.
Etherious Natsu
Dragneel, or E.N.D.
Your friend is the culmination
of decades of work.
The incarnation of his brother,
and his mightiest demon.
His Demons have one purpose.
It's like a homing instinct.
Once triggered, they
become single minded.
[INVEL] Their only thought
is that Zeref...
...must die.
[GRAY]
I can't believe it.
My mortal enemy has been
right here beside me.
[NATSU]
Move, Gray.
[GRAY] You're the one who took
everything away from me.
My family. Ur.
You and those other
demons took it all.
And now Juvia's gone.
I said move.
[GRAY]
This ends now, Natsu.
Nobody else dies,
except for you!
Get out of my way!
[BOTH growling]
[BOTH yell]
[yelling]
Well, your magic is
really something else.
Those injuries were
severe moments ago.
[BRANDISH]
I can shrink my wounds,
but I'm afraid I can't fix all
the damage that's been done.
[EVERGREEN]
So her time-stopping spell
didn't work on Natsu, huh?
I had no idea just how
powerful he'd become.
If only I had the ability
to shrink my confusion.
I just don't know what
to do about everything.
[LUCY]
That's completely normal.
Life can seem impossible
to navigate sometimes.
But it's really an
opportunity to grow.
[HAPPY]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
So I wouldn't see it
as a bad thing.
All it means is you're trying
to live to your fullest.
[HAPPY]
Let's go, Lucy!
[LUCY]
Yeah!
You girls stay here.
We're gonna go and find Natsu!
We'll talk some
sense into him!
[JUVIA]
My darling's out here.
Confused and alone.
I'm so worried. I just
hope I'm not too late.
[yells]
No, Gray! You won't stop me!
Hey. Lucy.
Open your eyes.
Come on, wake up.
Please. Lucy!
No one can stop me!
Oh, yeah? You're wrong, Natsu!
I'll stop you for good!
[groaning]
Master!
Is everything okay?
[MAKAROV] Don't worry about
me, just keep moving!
That's not gonna be easy!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
There's wave after
wave of them!
They just keep on coming!
[ERZA]
Don't be afraid!
I'll carve a path for you!
--It's Erza!
--Oh, yeah!
[WIZARD A laughs]
[MAKAROV]
Thank you.
[ERZA] Master, don't push
yourself too hard.
Together, we'll make it
back to the guild hall.
Of course we will.
I'm no fool.
What in the--?
Whoa! A giant eyeball?
[gasps]
[IRENE]
You can try to hide, Mavis,
but it will only prove futile.
Nothing escapes
my all-seeing eye.
I'll find you.
[WIZARD D]
It can talk!
[WIZARD E]
Who's Mavis?
[WIZARD F]
They're after the First Master!
[YUKINO]
This power... it feels familiar.
Like the wizard from
the northern front.
[ANGEL squeals]
The Scarlet Despair is here.
I've never seen
that kind of magic!
It's creepin' me out.
Me, too. It's so scary!
[MAVIS] I have no intention
of hiding from you!
Sounds like the First Master.
Where is she?
[gasps]
[MAVIS] You may have
control of our guild hall
for the time being.
But we will without
a doubt reclaim it!
[WIZARDS gasping]
Hear me, my guildmates
and brothers in arms.
We'll fight as one.
The Fairy Tactician will guide
your swords to their targets!
Holy--!
She's huge!
That's an illusion, right, guys?
Our First Master is showing
us all what she does best.
It's incredible.
[WIZARDS cheering]
She gives us inspiration
like no other.
And just like that,
morale rises tenfold.
So that's how it is.
She can sway them so easily
with only a few choice words.
What an insufferable
little bother.
[WIZARDS cheering]
[SOLDIER A, SOLDIER B yell]
[SOLDIER C groans]
[SOLDIER D]
Damnit! We're losin' ground!
[SOLDIER E] We still have
the numbers, men!
Push them back!
[IRENE]
Enchant.
[SOLDIERS groaning]
No.
What is this?
Why are all their
soldiers freaking out?
This is bad. Oh, no!
[snarling]
[chuckles]
[IRENE]
Berserker.
[gasps]
[WARREN]
Erza!
The soldiers' abilities
have been enhanced!
[WIZARDS screaming]
We're screwed.
There's way more of 'em.
And they all got stronger.
[BESERKERS snarling]
[IRENE] My berserker spell
enhances one's fighting ability
many times over.
They're basically mindless
killing machines now.
So, tell me, Mavis,
what's your move?
Yes. You're outnumbered
and overpowered.
Damn! What do we do?
They're shredding our defenses!
[yells]
That's the Giant Armor!
And Spear of Haja!
Erza, way to go!
Show em' what you're made of!
Requip! Flame Empress Armor!
[ERZA]
Thunder Empress Armor!
[WIZARDS cheering]
Purgatory Armor!
[ERZA yells]
[gasps]
[snarling]
They got back up!
[WIZARD P]
You gotta be kidding!
[WIZARDS screaming]
I don't think they
can feel pain.
Oh, man, we're screwed!
No, Dad!
Open your eyes, please!
Come on!
[MAKAROV]
So this is how it ends.
Master! We have to stay strong!
I will carve a path!
My journey will end here,
while my children go on.
That stance he's
taking... Fairy Law!
Oh, yeah! Take 'em all out!
We've got this in the bag, now!
You got this, Master!
Thank goodness!
[MAVIS]
Don't do it!
[WIZARD G]
First Master?
[WIZARD H]
Why shouldn't he?
[WIZARD C]
It's the only chance we've got!
It's too risky!
The more enemies
the spell targets,
the more it drains
your lifeforce away!
This army is massive!
There's no way
you'll survive it!
Is that true?
He'll die.
We can take care of 'em, Master!
It's just gonna
take some muscle!
Trust me. I'm painfully aware
of the toll this will take.
Let me have this.
One final blaze of glory.
But I have a plan!
I know of a way
we can avoid this!
You don't have to die!
[MAKAROV]
Shut your mouth!
My children are suffering
before my very eyes.
I have to end their pain.
Their lives are in my hands!
You may see them as soldiers,
or pieces in some game,
but to me, they're family.
My own flesh and blood!
No, I-I don't--
[MAKAROV] I realize that
any plan you may propose
will result in our
ultimate victory,
but I can't wait
for that outcome.
Not while my children's
blood is shed.
And so I have to end this!
An old soldier like me
has little time left,
and if it means the young
can go on living...
...I'll gladly pay that price.
Master!
Erza. Listen to me.
No, please! Don't do it!
Keep going! Let me
lead you back home!
[MAKAROV]
Although you may face
what seem like
insurmountable odds,
you will find the way forward
if you work together.
Trust in yourself.
But don't forget that
you're not alone.
This guild is a family.
The bond you share
is unbreakable.
My journey has been one
filled with happiness...
...and love...
...thanks to all of you.
Master!
[MAKAROV]
I will die leaving no regrets.
Please, kids.
Take care of each other.
So it's a parent's duty to stand
up in front of their children.
And though they may tremble,
plant their feet firmly
into the ground.
I will not allow you to
have our First Master!
Let's go help the First Master!
We're not giving a monster
like you a drop of alcohol.
You should respect her
more than anyone else!
I apologize.
It feels good to be
with my family again!
As long as I draw breath, I'll
protect my family at any cost!
And that is what it
means to be a parent.
[MAKAROV]
Fairy Law.
It got really quiet
all of a sudden.
I know. Wonder what happened.
What was that? I thought
I heard something.
That light... It's strange.
[ANGEL]
I can hardly see a thing.
Me, too.
That felt like something big.
[PORLYUSICA]
Yes.
Fool.
That damned fool.
Cute!
You really want me to name him?
That would be a priceless gift.
[MAVIS]
Makarov.
It's from a story
I read as a child.
[MAVIS]
The name of a kind-hearted king.
[crying]
Get up, First Master.
Stand strong.
We all still have a fight ahead.
And if we wanna win
this one, we need you.
It's what the old
geezer would want.
[ERZA]
Know this...
Being your child... has been
my life's greatest honor.
How many men did
we lose just now?
If I had to guess,
I'd say 70 to 80%.
I must admit, that
is very impressive.
I gave them too little credit.
Mavis learned that
spell from me,
and it seems that she, in turn,
passed it on to Makarov.
[IRENE]
Luckily, the remaining members
of the Spriggan Twelve
were unaffected by it,
so we still have the advantage.
[yells]
[GRAY groans]
[growls]
[GRAY]
You won't get past me, Natsu.
You hear me?!
[yelling]
[screams]
[yells]
[yelling]
[gasps]
How can you do this right now?
At a time like this?
Erza.
She's crying.
[LUCY] Erza's tears stop the
fight between Natsu and Gray.
A reminder of all they've
shared over the years.
The joys and sorrows,
triumphs and heartbreaks.
The loving voice of their family
works its song into
the warriors' hearts,
warming them as it cools
the fires of hatred.
Meanwhile, led by the
remaining Twelve,
Alvarez continues its onslaught.
And launches a ferocious
assault on Ishgar.
Next Time: "Pleasure and Pain."
Love can cause extreme changes--
creating life or bringing death.