- Natsu:
PREVIOUSLY, ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Happy: JUST AS NIRVANA
WAS ABOUT TO FIRE
ON THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD,
ITS LEG WAS BLASTED
BY THE MAGIC BOMBER CHRISTINA,
CAUSING IT TO MISS ITS MARK.
- Lucy: THE TRIMEN, LYON
AND SHERRY USED THE LAST
OF THEIR MAGIC ENERGY
TO KEEP CHRISTINA IN THE AIR
AS LONG AS THEY POSSIBLY COULD.
- Carla: BUT NOW SHE'S CRASHED
TO THE GROUND.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
DEEP WITHIN THE WORTH WOODSEA,
A POWERFUL SPELL CAPABLE
OF SWITCHING LIGHT AND DARKNESS
KNOWN AS NIRVANA
WAS SEALED AWAY,
UNTIL A DARK GUILD
CALLED THE ORACION SEIS
WENT SEARCHING FOR IT,
DETERMINED TO UNSEAL AND OBTAIN
THIS POWERFUL MAGIC.
A COALITION OF OFFICIAL GUILDS
WAS ASSEMBLED IN AN EFFORT
TO STOP THEM.
FROM THE FAIRY TAIL GUILD--
NATSU, LUCY, GRAY AND ERZA.
FROM BLUE PEGASUS--
HIBIKI, REN, EVE AND ICHIYA.
FROM LAYMIA SCALE--
LYON, SHERRY AND JURA.
AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST,
FROM THE CAIT SHELTER GUILD,
WENDY MARVELL.
THOUGH PRESUMED DEAD AFTER
THE DESTRUCTION OF THE TOWER
OF HEAVEN, JELLAL HAS RETURNED.
AND HIS PRESENCE HAS THROWN
OUR HEROES INTO UTTER CONFUSION.
AFTER MANY BATTLES, THE DARK
GUILD HAS BEEN DEFEATED.
BUT NATSU AND HIS FRIENDS
FIND THEMSELVES
IN THEIR WORST PREDICAMENT YET
WHEN MASTER ZERO MAKES
AN APPEARANCE.
- I'LL TAKE ONE.
- TWO.
- I GUESS I'LL TAKE THREE.
PLEASE DON'T LET ZERO BE THERE.
- THEN I SHALL TAKE NUMBER FOUR.
I CAN TELL IT'S THE CLOSEST
TO ME,
THANKS TO THE SMELL
OF ITS PARFUM.
- YOU MEAN, BECAUSE YOU SEE IT
ON THE MAP?
- MY HONEY, WHY DO YOU INSIST
ON MAKING A FOOL OUT OF ME?
- I CAN TAKE NUMBER FIVE.
YOU'RE LEFT WITH NUMBER SIX.
- ( Narrator speaking )
- ( wind howling )
- Gray:
( panting ) JEEZ.
IT'S LIKE THIS HALLWAY'S
NEVER ENDING.
I WAS WORRIED I WASN'T
GONNA MAKE IT.
I GUESS THIS IS LACRIMA
NUMBER TWO.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA
BE EASY ENOUGH TO DESTROY.
NO SIGN OF MASTER ZERO.
IT'S ABOUT TIME I CATCH A BREAK.
BUT THAT MEANS ONE
OF THE OTHERS
IS GOING HEAD-TO-HEAD
WITH THAT PSYCHO RIGHT NOW.
- Narrator: MEANWHILE,
BACK AT LACRIMA NUMBER ONE.
- ( groaning )
JELLAL!
- WELL, HELLO.
I TAKE IT YOUR MEMORY
HAS RETURNED?
- YES.
- ( growls )
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE COME HERE.
JELLAL!
- STOP.
- DID YOU FORGET FLAMES
DON'T WORK ON ME?
- YES, BRIEFLY,
BUT I REMEMBERED JUST IN TIME.
ONLY YOU CAN STOP ZERO.
- WHAT?
- CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG,
BUT AS A FIRE DRAGON SLAYER,
DOESN'T THE POWER
OF FLAME AMPLIFY YOUR MAGIC?
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
BUT WHY?
- LIAR.
JUDGING BY YOUR ACTIONS,
YOUR MEMORY HAS
NOT BEEN RESTORED.
- I DIDN'T LIE TO YOU.
ONLY MY MEMORIES
OF NATSU HAVE RETURNED.
I'M DETERMINED
TO STOP NIRVANA.
WHETHER OR NOT THE REST
OF MY MEMORIES RETURN
WILL NOT AFFECT MY GOAL.
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- WHEN I AWOKE,
IT WAS AS THOUGH MY MEMORY
HAD BEEN COMPLETELY WIPED CLEAN.
ALTHOUGH I HAVE NO RECOLLECTION
OF BEHAVING LIKE A VILE CRETIN,
IT SEEMS THAT WAS THE CASE.
I'VE BROUGHT HARM UPON
NOT ONLY YOU AND ERZA,
BUT ALL OF FAIRY TAIL.
IT'S TIME TO MAKE AMENDS.
I WANT TO HELP YOU PROTECT
WENDY'S GUILD.
I WANT TO STOP NIRVANA.
I KNOW WE CAN DO IT AS LONG
AS WE WORK TOGETHER.
- I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU FORGOT
EVERYTHING YOU DID TO US?
QUIT PRETENDING TO BE
ON OUR SIDE OR YOU'LL PAY.
- NATSU, PLEASE, JUST ACCEPT THE
FLAMES I GAVE YOU AND MOVE ON.
- YOU MAY HAVE FORGOTTEN
WHAT HAPPENED IN THE PAST,
BUT THE REST OF US HAVEN'T.
I STILL REMEMBER EVERYTHING.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
THAT YOU MADE ERZA CRY.
- HOW PATHETIC.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO ARGUE,
MUST YOU DO IT IN FRONT OF ME?
QUIT WASTING MY TIME.
- ( Jellal grunting )
- WHY, JELLAL?
- ( panting )
JUST GO AHEAD AND KILL ME,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
I'M ALREADY BATTERED
AND TORN TO SHREDS.
BUT FIRST,
LET ME GIVE YOU THE POWER
YOU NEED TO DEFEAT HIM.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH A GOLDEN FLAME.
- Narrator: TWO OF OUR OTHER
HEROES ARE WORKING THEIR WAY
TOWARDS LACRIMA NUMBER THREE.
- Happy: YOU WANNA TAKE A BREAK
TO CATCH YOUR BREATH?
- I CAN'T.
WE WON'T MAKE IT IN TIME.
- GUESS NOT.  BUT YOU'RE BARELY
ABLE TO WALK RIGHT NOW.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- DON'T WORRY, I'M FINE.
I MAY BE SLOW,
BUT I WILL GET THERE.
PLUS, HERE'S THE THING.
IF I STOP, I DON'T KNOW IF I--
WELL.
LET'S NOT TALK ABOUT THIS NOW.
WE'VE GOTTA STAY FOCUSED.
- ( grunting ) MAN.  MAN.  MAN.
- Narrator: IN THE PASSAGEWAY
TO LACRIMA NUMBER FOUR.
- THIS IS EXHAUSTING,
BUT IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I'LL GET THERE IN TIME.
I'M ICHIYA VANDALAY KOTOBUKI
OF BLUE PEGASUS.
I WILL FULFILL MY DUTY
TO MY GUILD.
- Narrator:
AT LACRIMA NUMBER FIVE.
- MASTER ZERO ISN'T HERE.
I KNEW IT.
HE MUST BE AT LACRIMA
NUMBER ONE AFTER ALL.
NATSU.
- THIS IS THE FLAME OF REBUKE.
- Narrator: IN THE PASSAGEWAY
TO LACRIMA NUMBER SIX.
- THANK YOU FOR DOING THIS,
CARLA.
I'M WORRIED.
I HOPE JELLAL'S OKAY.
- PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
BE MORE CONCERNED
WITH YOUR OWN WELL-BEING.
THIS WON'T BE EASY.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH. I'M THE ONE
WHO CAUSED THIS
SO I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO MAKE IT RIGHT.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU NOT FEELING WELL?
- I'M FINE.
FORGIVE ME IF I'M WRONG,
BUT DON'T YOU USE HEALING MAGIC?
- NATSU'S GOING TO FACE ZERO.
SO HE'LL NEED HIS
ENERGY REPLENISHED.
THINK YOU CAN DO THAT FOR HIM?
- I'LL TRY.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
DRAINING USING HER HEALING MAGIC
CAN BE AND HOW MANY TIMES THIS
POOR GIRL HAD TO USE IT TODAY?
SORRY,
BUT I'M PUTTING MY FOOT DOWN.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- YOU DO?
- IT'S FINE.  I CAN REPLENISH
HIS ENERGY MYSELF.
I'VE GAINED A MEMORY.
I REMEMBER WHAT MAKES THIS
NATSU FELLOW SO SPECIAL.
HE HOLDS THE POWER OF HOPE.
IT'S A LOT TO ASK,
BUT I NEED YOU TO DESTROY
LACRIMA NUMBER SIX FOR ME.
- ME?  BUT I CAN'T.
- WHY MUST YOU DOUBT YOURSELF?
YOU'RE A DRAGON SLAYER.
YOUR MAGIC IS SO POWERFUL,
IT WAS ONCE USED AGAINST
THE MOST TERRIFYING DRAGONS
IN THE LAND.
CONSUME THE AIR--
NO, THE HEAVENS.
UNLEASH THE POWER
OF THE DRAGON
THAT LIES DORMANT
WITHIN YOU.
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
I'M GONNA UNLEASH MY POWER.
THE DRAGON INSIDE ME.
I HAVE TO,
TO PROTECT MY GUILD.
IF YOU CAN HEAR ME GRANDINA,
PLEASE LEND ME YOUR POWER.
- WENDY.
- WHAT'S THE FLAME OF REBUKE?
- I'M NOT ASKING YOU
TO GRANT FORGIVENESS.
ALL I WANT IS TO GIVE YOU
STRENGTH,
BECAUSE I BELIEVE IN YOU.
ERZA TRUSTS YOU MORE
THAN ANYONE,
AND SO I SHALL AS WELL.
- ( grunting )
- WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU.
- THANKS FOR THE CHOW.
THIS DOESN'T MEAN YOU'RE
OFF THE HOOK, JELLAL.  NOT YET.
- YOU'VE MADE A GRAVE MISTAKE.
BY EATING THE FLAME OF REBUKE,
YOU NOW SHARE THE SINS
OF YOUR MORTAL ENEMY.
- A COUPLE OF SINS
AIN'T GONNA SCARE ME.
EVERYONE IN FAIRY TAIL'S
GOT THEIR SHARE.
BUT THE REAL SIN IS TURNING YOUR
BACK ON SOMEONE
WHEN THEY JUST WANNA HELP.
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY'LL GIVE
YOU THE POWER TO FIGHT EVIL.
- ( screams )
SO MUCH POWER.
NO, IT COULDN'T BE.
DRAGON FORCE.
- MAN, THAT LACRIMA IS
BIGGER THAN I THOUGHT.
THIS IS GONNA BE TOUGH.
- I SENSE A STRONG MAGIC POWER,
DO YOU?
- YEAH, THE LACRIMA
MUST BE CLOSE.
- I'VE CAUGHT A WHIFF
OF ITS PERILOUS PARFUM.
ALMOST THERE.  MAN!
- THE TIME DRAWS NEAR.
NATSU, I HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
- Carla: REMEMBER,
YOU HAVE TO STAY FOCUSED.
- I CAN DO IT.
NATSU.
- ( clamoring )
- OH, MAN.
IT'S LIKE WHEN I ATE
ALL THAT ETHERION.
AWESOME.
ALL OF A SUDDEN
IT FEELS LIKE MY STRENGTH'S BEEN
DOUBLED, MAYBE EVEN TRIPLED.
- I NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D HAVE IT.
DRAGON FORCE IS THE FINAL FORM
OF DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC.
FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
IT GIVES THE SLAYER DESTRUCTIVE
POWER COMPARABLE
TO THAT OF THE MOST
FORMIDABLE DRAGON.
I'M INTRIGUED.
SO SHOW ME.
- YOU SURE YOU WANT ME
TO DO THAT?
- YES.
LET'S SEE THE DRAGON'S POWER.
- ALL RIGHT, BUT I WARNED YOU.
- ( sobbing )
WE DID IT.
WE MADE IT TO THE LACRIMA.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU GOTTA HANG IN THERE.
- HONESTLY, I DIDN'T WANT
TO ADMIT IT EARLIER.
I'M NOT SO SURE
I CAN EVEN DO THIS.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WELL, I'M COMPLETELY OUT
OF MAGIC ENERGY.
BUT I'VE GOTTA DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO HELP PROTECT WENDY'S GUILD.
I DON'T WANNA LET
THE OTHERS DOWN.
THEY CAN'T WIN.
THE ORACION SEIS CAN'T BEAT US.
- LUCY!
- I'VE COME THIS FAR.
I'M NOT READY
TO THROW IN THE TOWEL.
- BE CAREFUL.
- I HAVE TO TRY MY HARDEST.
FOR THE MEMBERS
OF CAIT SHELTER.
FOR JELLAL, WHO TAUGHT ME
TO BELIEVE IN MYSELF.
FOR NATSU
AND ALL MY NEW FRIENDS.
- YOU'RE NO MATCH
FOR DARK GRAVITY.
- ( screams )
- DON'T TELL ME
I'VE ALREADY DEFEATED
THE MIGHTY DRAGON SLAYER.
WELL?
- NATSU.
- YIKES.  THAT WAS CLOSE.
- ZERO SLASH!
DARK DELETE!
- ( laughs )
- ( grunting ) MAN.  MAN.
MAN. MAN.  MAN!
SO CLOSE.  I CANNOT BLACKOUT
AFTER I'VE MADE IT THIS FAR.
- HIBIKI, REN,
EVE, I ASK THAT
YOU LEND ME THE STRENGTH
TO GET THROUGH THIS.
- ( grunts )
- THREE MINUTES LEFT.
- NATSU.
- ( Zero grunting )
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT'S THE
BEST YOUR DRAGON FORCE CAN DO?
DRAGONS ONCE RULED
THIS WORLD
AND THAT'S THE EXTENT OF
THEIR POWER?  WHAT A TRAVESTY!
- ( panting )
- SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
ANY IDEA?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I WON'T GIVE UP.
I'LL THROW MYSELF AGAINST IT.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
I MAY BE TIRED.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT,
I'LL DO WHAT I SAID I'D DO.
- WE'VE ALWAYS ADMIRED YOUR
DETERMINATION, MISS LUCY.
- ( gasps )
- PIRI, PIRI. WE ARE INSPIRED
BY YOUR RESOLVE.
- AND WE ARE DEEPLY MOVED
BY YOUR EMOTION.
- GEMINI.
WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE
YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
- ( both scream )
- WHEN WE COPY YOU, WE NOT ONLY
SHARE YOUR APPEARANCE,
BUT YOUR ABILITIES.
WE'RE PERFECTLY CAPABLE
OF DOING THE JOB FOR YOU.
- AYE!
- IN THREE MINUTES, WE'RE GONNA
SMASH THAT THING TO BITS.
- THANK YOU, GEMINI.
- MAN! MAN!
I FINALLY MADE IT.
NOW TO TAKE A WHIFF
OF MY PARFUM OF POWER.
( grunts )
- IT'S NOT QUITE ENOUGH.
I NEED MORE POWER
FROM THE HEAVENS.
- YOU CANNOT DEFEAT THE MASTER
OF THE ORACION SEIS.
I'M MORE POWERFUL THAN
A LOWLY GUILD WIZARD LIKE YOU
COULD EVER HOPE TO BE.
IT'S A SHAME YOUR FRIENDS
AREN'T HERE TO HELP YOU,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST ME ON YOUR OWN.
- ( panting )
I'M NOT ON MY OWN.
EVERYONE'S REACHING OUT TO ME.
I CAN HEAR THEM
LOUD AND CLEAR.
I HEAR EVERYONE'S VOICES,
AND THEY'RE TELLING ME
THAT NO MATTER WHAT,
I CAN'T GIVE UP THE FIGHT.
THEY'RE WHAT KEEPS ME GOING.
THEY'RE THE ONLY REASON
I'M STILL STANDING RIGHT NOW.
- WELL, ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ABOUT TIME
TO PUT THIS THING ON ICE.
- OKAY, LET'S DO IT.
IS IT ALL RIGHT IF I USE TAURUS?
- SURE, GO AHEAD.
- YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET AN
IMPORTANT LESSON IN STRENGTH
AND DETERMINATION, COURTESY
OF THE BLUE PEGASUS GUILD.
- REQUIP!
- I CAN FEEL IT.
THE POWER WELLING UP
INSIDE OF ME.
- DEAR CHILD.
- THEY'RE SO STRONG.
I CAN FEEL MY FRIENDS'
DETERMINATION AND STRENGTH
PULSATING THROUGH ME!
- IF THERE WERE SOME WAY,
IF I COULD HARNESS THE POWER
OF YOUR DRAGON FORCE FOR MYSELF.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
SINCE I HAVE NO USE FOR YOU, I
SHALL UNLEASH MY ULTIMATE SPELL
AND RETURN YOU
TO THE NOTHINGNESS
FROM WHENCE YOU CAME.
DRAGON SLAYER SECRET ART.
FLAME LOTUS,
EXPLODING FLAME BLADE!
GENESIS ZERO!
- ( screaming )
NOW TO THE DEPTHS OF NOTHINGNESS
WITH YOU.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Natsu: YOU THINK THERE MIGHT
BE A PLACE
WHERE DRAGONS JUST WALK AROUND
LIKE IT'S NO BIG DEAL?
- Happy: MAYBE,
BUT I HIGHLY DOUBT IT, NATSU.
- IT'D BE AWESOME IF THERE WERE,
'CAUSE THEN I COULD PRACTICE
MY DRAGON SLAYER MAGIC
ALL THE TIME.
- HA!  WHO NEEDS A PUNY DRAGON
WHEN YOU'VE GOT
A STRONG, HEROIC CAT LIKE ME?
- I DON'T THINK YOU REALIZE WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING YOURSELF INTO.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Natsu: I WOULDN'T FEEL RIGHT
PRACTICING MY MAGIC ON YOU.
- Happy: HOW COME? I'LL SHOW
YOU I'M JUST AS STRONG
AS ANY SILLY OL' DRAGON.
- Natsu: WHATEVER YOU SAY, PAL.