[chuckles]
You seem tired.
That makes it my turn.
Let's end this!
That's what you came for, right?
Feed me with your pain!
Every whimper charges my whip!
[LUCY] Please stop...
Beg away, but there's
no safety word with me!
That would ruin the fun!
[laughs]
Down, girl!
[screaming]
[laughing]
If you're lookin' for us,
we're over here!
It's hide and go seek!
We didn't come here
to play silly children's games!
Especially not with these two
annoying little rugrats.
[GEMI] Piri, piri.
These guys aren't
any fun at all.
[MINI]
Yeah, they're really boring.
Piri, piri, pikkiri!
It's blinding me!
The first to win two
out of a total of three matches
shall be declared the victor.
Is this agreeable to you?
Yes, it is.
But before we begin in earnest,
allow me to
compliment your stagecraft.
The extra context makes me
all the more determined to win.
[SAGITTARIUS] We are
warriors, the both of us.
It's been my experience that a
warrior only fights at his best
when taken by
the mood of battle.
Intriguing.
My experience has been the same.
Well, then.
It seems we're
more alike than I knew.
[SAGITTARIUS]
I appreciate that.
If all else is settled,
then tell me:
Are you prepared
for battle?
A good warrior
is always ready for battle.
A small part of me does wish
we had an audience, though.
I considered bringing one in,
but I don't have the heart
to destroy you so publicly.
This is my way
of showing you mercy.
Ooh, I hope your sword's
as sharp as your tongue.
Erza Scarlet, I challenge you!
I accept!
[hamster wheel running]
That's not gonna
help anything, you know.
Well, I gotta do something
or I'm gonna lose my mind!
Actually, I think I
must've already lost my mind,
because there's no way
I would ever let myself
end up in this crazy situation!
And if anybody in
the guild saw me like this,
I'd lose my reputation
along with it!
I just think you're
wasting your energy
running in that thing
instead of thinking
of how to get outta here.
I'm not gonna get any ideas
by just layin'
around on my butt!
This sucks!
How in the hell are we gonna
bust outta this stupid cage,
get back to normal,
and seal up these brats
before anybody sees us?
[GEMI] Hey, it looks
like the hairy one's playing!
[MINI]
Run faster, little guy!
They are just so cute!
They're ridiculously cute!
[HAPPY] Erza vs. Sagittarius!
Horseback Showdown!
Piri, piri!
[PANTHERLILY]
Stop that nonsense!
Let us out right now!
You better
turn us back to normal
so we can give
you little blue punks
the spankings you deserve!
[giggles]
It sounds like
they're startin' to get
kinda grumpy in there.
Too bad.
I bet the
precious widdle cuties
are just hungry, is all. So sad.
Here ya go!
Now open wide!
[GEMI] Now eat up!
[GAJEEL] Get that stuff
outta my face!
I ain't eatin' no grass!
We just picked this
a minute ago,
so it's nice and fresh
and nummy for your tummy!
I just told ya,
I don't eat this crap!
Gimme some iron, if ya got it!
Now, don't be so stubborn!
Eat up all of your weeds
like a good little boy!
If you don't eat 'em,
you're never gonna grow up
to be big and strong,
now, will you?
[GAJEEL] Listen up, rugrats!
Eatin' weeds ain't my thing!
I need iron!
So these kids think
we're their pets?
This is so embarrassing!
[GEMI] Wow, your tail
is so soft and fluffy!
[MINI] Who wants
his widdle belly rubbed?
[GAJEEL] Stop touching me!
I'm seriously gonna
bite your fingers off!
He's like the
fuzziest little guy
in the whole entire world!
I just wanna
pinch his tiny cheeks!
We wanna play
with you forever!
Stop yankin' on me! That hurts!
They're the absolute
worst kind of pet owners.
I mean, what kind
of maniac would pick up
a tiny little animal like that
and then start trying
to yank them to pieces?
You gotta be gentle,
or else the thing's
gonna get hurt.
C'mon, pal! Help me out!
This is going against
everything I believe in,
but I can't just sit back
and watch this happen.
See? I love to frolic, too!
I think that somebody's
getting jealous!
Now the little one wants us
to start playing with him!
Aw, what a fuzzy-wuzzy
widdle cutie pie!
Gah!
[GEMI, MINI]
We'll play with you!
No, come back here!
The hairy one
got out of the cage,
so we gotta go
and get him right now!
[MINI]
Aww... Don't worry.
It's okay!
He won't get very far!
Don't forget that there are
a buncha super scary
animals outside.
All those bears and boars
and wolves and stuff.
You'd better not leave me
here with these crazy kids.
[GAJEEL] When I'm normal,
I gotta go back and
save Lily as soon as I can!
[GEMI, MINI]
No, don't go!
Piri, piri, pikkiri!
No!
Now I'm a freakin' frog?
You're not hoppin' away from us!
You know, I really don't think
that frogs are very cute.
So let's try something else!
[GAJEEL] Really? A snail?
I'm never gonna
outrun those little brats!
Nice work!
That is so much cuter
than the froggie!
Yeah, he's adorable!
But I still think
I'd like him better
if he was fluffier!
[MINI] That's pretty cute,
but watch this!
I'm getting
really sick of cute!
Plus, there's no way
I can fight like this,
so I gotta get back
to awesome, like, meow!
[stomping noise]
Meow?
Meow!
Oh, you clowns
ain't getting' in my way!
Listen up, furball.
Uh-huh?
I'm gonna need you to
help me take care of a problem.
Uh-huh...
Oh, boo.
I'm afraid he might have
really gotten away from us.
We made him too fast.
Come back, fuzzy!
Hey! I think I found him!
Piri, piri!
[GEMI]
Ya can't hide from us!
[MINI] We see you!
[GEMI, MINI] Piri?
Time for sweet payback!
[screams]
That's so not fair!
That really hurt,
ya big meanie!
Now we gotta
teach the bad ol' kitty
not to do things like that!
Take this!
--Bad kitty!
[GEMI, MINI] Pikkiri!
Me-ow!
Whoa, you turned me
into a mongoose!
And it looks like you
turned me into a creepy snake!
[GEMI]
Oh, but you sure do look
super duper yummy
to me right now!
--[MINI] No, please!
--[GEMI] Stay still!
--I'm not a snake for real!
--Just give me a little nibble!
All right!
This kitty's got
way more than claws!
Iron Dragon Club!
--Piri?
[GEMI, MINI] Piri!
[GAJEEL] Man, I really
wish I woulda realized
I could still use magic
from the very beginning.
Now get lost, will ya?
[GEMI, MINI] Piri!
I feel like myself again.
Nicely done, Gajeel.
Thanks, Lily.
But couldn't you
have just used
your Iron Dragon Club
from the very beginning
of this whole ordeal?
Shut up!
I just assumed I
wouldn't be able to, okay?
[ARCADIOS]
It would seem very likely
that Leo is keeping watch
over the celestial globe.
[HISUI] So if we can
manage to get a sense
of where the globe
is being hidden,
he should be somewhere nearby.
Let's go see
if we can locate it.
[ARCADIOS]
Please wait, princess.
I brought a portable
projection lacrima-tron with me.
It is a rather
basic model, however.
Excellent idea.
Shall we test it out?
It appears that
the celestial spirits
are still rebelling.
If only we could use this
to pinpoint Leo's location.
Perhaps there's a hidden chamber
somewhere deep within
the Astral Spiritus itself?
There's something else
that's been troubling me
about the situation.
What's on your mind, princess?
We've been dealing with
the twelve zodiac spirits.
But that's not all that exist.
There's another one:
The spirit that passes
through the thirteenth gate.
The snake charmer. Ophiuchus.
It's very possible
that they could be
involved in this as well.
A good point.
We need to
account for that one
and verify my suspicion.
[HISUI] My feeling is they
could be playing a crucial role.
But what are they doing?
I'm one of the few
celestial wizards left.
And what's more,
my irresponsible actions
got us into this mess.
I have to make
things right again.
Princess Hisui...
[VIRGO] We're not playing
hide and go seek, you know.
That's not my kind
of game at all.
I've got a super-sized
helping of punishment
that I'm just dying to serve up.
So come and get it!
[LUCY] I really
don't want to fight her.
But I can't hide here forever.
I need to think
of a plan, quickly.
I've got mayo. Come on!
[VIRGO]
This room is perfect.
So many places to hide.
[thumping noise]
Uh-oh!
I will not have
my gate closed for me,
thank you very much.
Now be a good girl
and hand over the key.
I'll just use
my Fleuve d'étoiles!
[chuckling]
[LUCY] No matter what, I can't
let her have this key!
We'll just have to pass
on the mayo for now!
You can never run away
from your fate, Miss Lucy.
I thought I could
get through this
without having to fight you.
But you've left me
with no other options.
Sorry, but this
is for your own good!
[ERZA] Excuse me,
but I have one
question before we begin.
[SAGITTARIUS]
And what would that be?
[ERZA] You wish to
complete the Liberam ritual,
which will supposedly
grant you freedom.
But then your
life will be reduced
to a mere twelve days.
That's such a brief time.
So my question is this:
Is your freedom
so valuable to you
that you are willing
to forfeit your life?
If it means I die
free and unencumbered
by my forced
servitude to humanity,
then yes, that is a trade
I am more than willing to make.
Before this rebellion began,
you celestial spirits
had all formed
a strong bond of
friendship with Lucy.
Do you truly see her
as an oppressor now?
I have no
recollection of this bond.
The idea that we'd be
friends with a human
that used us as tools
for their convenience
sounds like rubbish to me.
It wasn't like that.
Lucy deeply cares for you,
even still.
My resolve
will never be swayed
by this emotional drivel.
That is the noble
path of the warrior.
[ERZA sighs]
If there is no other way...
We will engage in
a total of three matches.
The first one to win two
of these will be the victor.
Do you accept these terms?
Yes, I accept.
[SAGITTARIUS] Now let us
begin the first match!
[ERZA] Horseback archery?
Very well.
Ah! Splendid!
That is quite a fascinating
steed you have there.
Well, this will be
a once in a lifetime battle.
I hope you're
prepared to give
this competition your all.
A true warrior
always strives to win.
Let me show you
how this is done.
Impressive.
[SAGITTARIUS]
Go ahead and take your turn.
It would appear
that I have been bested.
You're an awfully
graceful competitor.
It is an integral part
of the warrior's
code of conduct.
To engage in battle
is a sacred act.
However!
There're still two matches left!
The real battle
has only just begun!
[ERZA] I'm assuming the
second round will be a race?
Indeed.
Keep inside your lane,
and the first one
to the finish line
will be declared the victor.
Fine.
We'll begin at my signal.
Get ready... Go!
He's fast!
I'm afraid this weight puts me
at a severe disadvantage.
Goal!
[ERZA] Congratulations.
I feel very fortunate to
have met such a capable rival.
I truly appreciate
your words of praise.
But we are now tied
with a score of one to one
going into the final round.
Which will be...
...an armed battle between
two warriors on horseback!
Whoever wins this one
takes total victory.
But be aware...
A large quantity
of explosives
have been placed at random
all over this beach.
Even I have no knowledge
of where they may be.
So proceed with caution.
I appreciate the information.
Now for my choice of weapon.
[SAGITTARIUS]
Shall we begin?
[ERZA] I'm ready!
I must say, you're an
extremely skilled warrior,
but will it be enough?
You're aware that
spears can be used
for more than parrying blows?
Your reflexes are quite fast!
But your strength cannot
hold a candle to mine!
Perhaps, but your
brute force is completely wasted
if you're too slow
to hit your target!
Got you now!
Without your steed,
you've simply no chance
of claiming victory!
Surrender and
accept defeat gracefully.
I will never surrender to you!
All your determination
means nothing
if you are blown to smithereens
by your carelessness!
He told me he didn't know
where the
explosives were placed.
But how has he been able
to avoid triggering them
all this time?
Horses are very
sensitive creatures!
I can avoid them by
following my instincts!
My weapon!
You've lost
your steed, your steel,
and you're surrounded
by explosives.
You're left with
no safe place to stand.
I'm afraid you're
wrong about that, sir.
There's one place I can go.
[ERZA] On your back!
No explosives here, right?
[SAGITTARIUS]
How disrespectful!
I will not tolerate
anyone treating me
like some lowly farm animal!
This armor is
too heavy to be of use!
Yes, much more appropriate!
I won't stand for this!
Get off of me this instant!
I'd rather deal
with you thrashing about
than take my chances
getting blown to bits!
Giddyup!
Hiyah!
Keep moving and don't
slow down for anything!
[ERZA] I'll wager there aren't
any explosives past this point!
[yelling]
Well, it seems
I was wrong about that.
You fought well, Sagittarius,
but victory is mine.
[SAGITTARIUS] Thank you.
I knew that you would
be a worthy adversary,
but I did expect to win.
I humbly concede
defeat in this battle.
My fate is now in your hands,
so administer whatever
justice you see fit.
You have proven yourself to be
a most valiant opponent as well.
You have my utmost respect,
but I do hope to
see you return to normal.
Forced Closure!
I wonder how Natsu
and the others are faring.
What the heck is that thing?
An operating table?
It's a far
more sophisticated
piece of equipment than that.
In fact, it collects
the patients
and prepares them for surgery.
--[WENDY, CARLA scream]
--Let go of them!
What are you
gonna do to us?
I'm sure it'll
be bad for our health!
All of you need
something removed, I'm sure!
Don't let this thing catch you!
Run away!
Man, you're seriously gonna
have to do better than that!
Oh, is that the case?
Whoa!
As I told you earlier,
I am the solely
designated caretaker
of the Astral Spiritus.
So that means I also have a
great deal of dominance over it.
I got ya!
No...
That should be impossible!
All right, Happy,
full steam ahead!
[HAPPY] Aye, sir!
Fire Dragon Iron Fist!
Wow, thanks a lot, Natsu!
Yes, thank you.
I would much prefer not
to be dissected by that maniac.
It's not over yet!
[LOKE]
It is for now, Ophiuchus!
It's him!
About time you showed up!
The ceremony is
almost ready to begin.
It won't be necessary for you to
keep them occupied any longer,
so you may go now.
I understand, sir.
I take my leave.
They're really
about to start it?
I've got some
bad news for you,
all your cronies
are getting kicked back
into the celestial world
one-by-one as we speak!
And you can't hold your
little ceremony without them!
[chuckling, distant rumbling]
Oh. That's probably
not a good sound, is it?
The power of
darkness knows no bounds
and has given us another
chance to perform the Liberam!
We will not
give up our dream.
And we will not rest
until we have attained
true and absolute freedom!
[LOKE] Although we may
face setbacks along the way,
our hearts are unwavering!
We will cast off the shackles
humanity has placed upon us!
[NATSU] We're outside?
[WENDY] Yeah, but something
doesn't smell right!
[NATSU] Would you just
stay in one place already?
[LOKE] Ophiuchus!
The time has come
to reveal your true form!
[WENDY]
What does that mean?
[HAPPY] Hey, look!
I thought she
seemed too important
to just disappear like that.
The snake-charmer is
an absolutely vital part
of the zodiac.
So my true form is every bit as
majestic as that would entail.
In fact, the very place
known as the Astral Spiritus
is fully contained
within my body.
Everything that
has transpired so far
has been inside my body.
You coming here was by design.
A trap to lure you in!
[laughing evilly]
[LOKE] And now we
can perform the Liberam,
which will free us from the
human world once and for all!
There is nothing
you can do to stop us!
[OPHIUCHUS]
Oh, Celestial Spirit King.
I will not fail you!
I've heard of
someone being called a snake,
but this is ridiculous!
[HAPPY] I'm scared, Natsu!
How in the heck
are we gonna fight
against something that gigantic?
[NATSU]
One step at a time, buddy!
First we take out Loke
so we can stop him
from doing that ceremony!
[HAPPY] Yeah, I guess if we
keep him from finishing that,
we'll have one less thing
to worry about!
[NATSU] He's always been
kind of a jerk anyway,
so let's kick his butt!
[HAPPY] Aye, Sir!
[HAPPY, NATSU]
Next Time: Natsu vs. Leo!
I'll beat him down,
stop the ritual from happening,
and get things back
to normal in no time!
[HAPPY] Attaboy, Natsu!