- HEY, GUYS, READY FOR
SOME MORE "FAIRY TAIL"?
JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING,
YOU TURN THE LIGHTS ON
IN THE ROOM.
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV.
- Happy:
PREVIOUSLY ON "FAIRY TAIL"...
- Natsu: S-CLASS!
WE'RE GOING BIG TIME.
- Happy: WE CAME TO GALUNA
ISLAND ON AN S-CLASS QUEST
WITHOUT THE GUILD'S PERMISSION.
GRAY AND ERZA TRIED TO STOP US,
BUT THEY ENDED UP
GETTING INVOLVED.
WE DEFEATED THE DEMON DELIORA,
BUT NOW WE'VE GOT
A BIGGER PROBLEM.
- THE MOON!
IT MUST BE WIPED FROM THE SKY!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- NATSU, WE'RE GOING
TO DESTROY THE MOON.
- REALLY?!
- HUH?!
- IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN CHANGE
THE VILLAGERS BACK TO
THEIR HUMAN FORMS.
- ( all cheer )
- THEY'RE REALLY GONNA DO IT!
WE GET TO WATCH IT HAPPEN!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND WE'RE ALL FINALLY
GONNA BE HUMAN AGAIN!
- WHERE DO YOU WANNA GO?
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD CLIMB UP
TO THE TOP OF THE TEMPLE?
IT'S A LOT HIGHER UP THERE.
- WE'LL DO IT FROM HERE.
THE VILLAGERS CAN'T
GO NEAR THE TEMPLE,
AND THEY NEED
TO WITNESS THIS.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT SHE'S THINKING.
I MEAN, SHE CAN DO
SOME AMAZING THINGS, BUT STILL.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
SHE'S GONNA DO TO IT?
- THIS IS EXCITING, HUH?
- MORE LIKE TERRIFYING.
- ( Villagers chattering )
- THIS IS GIANT ARMOR.
IT INCREASES MY STRENGTH
AND ALLOWS ME TO THROW FARTHER.
AND THIS...
THIS IS THE SPEAR OF HAJA.
IT REPELS DARKNESS.
- Villagers: OHH...
- WHOA!  I SEE WHAT
YOU'RE PLANNING NOW.
YOU'RE GONNA USE THAT SPEAR
TO KNOCK THE MOON
OUT OF THE SKY.
- Natsu, Lucy, Happy:
GIVE ME A BREAK.
THAT'S NEVER GONNA WORK.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
BUT I'M AFRAID I'LL NEED
MORE STRENGTH
THAN THIS ARMOR CAN GIVE ME.
SO NATSU, I'M GOING TO NEED TO
USE YOUR FIRE POWER AS A BOOST.
- HUH?
- WHENEVER I BEGIN
TO THROW THE SPEAR,
I WANT YOU TO HIT
THE BACK OF IT WITH YOUR FLAMES.
- ( grunting )
- NOW I'LL HAVE TO TIME
OUR ATTACK PERFECTLY.
BUT I THINK YOU SHOULD GIVE ME
JUST ENOUGH POWER TO DO THE JOB.
- SOUNDS LIKE
A KILLER PLAN TO ME!
- THEN LET'S DO IT.
- WHOA...
- THEY DON'T REALLY THINK
THEY'RE GONNA
PULL THIS OFF, DO THEY?
- WELL, I THINK THEY'VE TOTALLY
GONE OFF THE DEEP END THIS TIME.
- ( Happy speaking )
- NOW!
- ( grunts )
- SHE DID IT!
- THIS IS BAD...
- WHAT ARE THEY THINKING?!
- ALMOST THERE!
- ( chattering excitedly )
- HA-HA-HA!
- ( all gasp )
( cheer )
- Both: NO WAY!
- ( all gasp )
- THE MOON...
- IT'S STILL THERE.
- ( all murmuring )
- IT WASN'T THE MOON
THAT SHATTERED.
IT WAS THE SKY.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT THE HECK
IS GOING ON?
- AS A RESULT OF THE SPELL,
A NOXIOUS MEMBRANE WAS
COVERING THE ISLAND.
- A WHAT?
- THE MOON DRIP
RELEASED EVIL ENERGY
IN THE FORM OF A GAS.
THAT GAS CRYSTALLIZED,
AND FORMED AN INVISIBLE SHELL
IN THE SKY
THAT COVERED THE ISLAND.
THAT'S WHY THE MOON
LOOKED PURPLE HERE.
- ( all murmuring )
- NOW THAT THE SHELL
HAS BEEN BROKEN,
EVERYTHING WILL GO BACK
TO HOW IT WAS THREE YEARS AGO.
- ( all gasping, chattering )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
THEY'RE NOT TRANSFORMING.
- OH, NO.
- THAT'S BECAUSE THESE
ARE THEIR TRUE FORMS.
- ( gasps )
THE MOON DRIP NEVER HAD
ANY EFFECT ON THEIR APPEARANCE.
HOWEVER, IT SEEMS TO HAVE
ALTERED THEIR MEMORIES.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THEY THINK THEY'RE HUMANS
WHO HAVE BEEN TRANSFORMED
INTO DEMONS.
BUT IT'S THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
- ( Happy and Lucy gasp )
- WAIT, SO YOU'RE SAYING...
THEY'RE REALLY...
- YEP, YOU'VE GOT IT.
- ( all scream )
- ( Villagers murmuring )
- THE VILLAGERS
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN DEMONS.
- AAH!
- HEY, IS THAT TRUE?
- WELL, MAYBE.
MY MEMORY'S HAZY.
WE ALL LOOKED PRETTY HUMAN
WHEN YOU MET US, DIDN'T WE?
- YES, BECAUSE YOU POSSESS THE
ABILITY TO TAKE ON HUMAN FORMS.
YOUR FALSE MEMORIES
LED YOU TO BELIEVE...
THAT YOUR TEMPORARY STATES
WERE ACTUALLY YOUR TRUE FORMS.
IN REALITY, YOU WERE DEMONS
WHO HAD FALLEN VICTIM
TO THE MOON DRIP'S
SIDE EFFECTS.
- HOLD ON.
HOW COME LYON AND THE OTHERS
WEREN'T AFFECTED?
- I ASSUME IT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE HUMAN.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
DEMONS WERE THE ONLY ONES
SUSCEPTIBLE TO THE MEMORY LOSS.
I KNEW WHAT WAS GOING ON
AS SOON AS THE VILLAGERS TOLD ME
THEY WERE UNABLE TO GO
TO THE TEMPLE.
THE MOONLIGHT COLLECTED THERE
WAS SACRED,
THEREFORE CREATURES OF
DARKNESS COULDN'T GO NEAR IT.
- YOU'RE QUITE THE DETECTIVE!
- (gasps)
- I KNEW I COULD TRUST YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS.
- AAH!
- THANKS, WIZARDS.
I OWE YOU ONE.
- A GHOST!
- YOU'RE THE GUY FROM THE BOAT.
- ( gasps )
- ( gasps ) BOBO...
- BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE--
- GETTING STABBED IN THE CHEST
HURT PRETTY BAD,
BUT YOU GOTTA DO MORE
THAN THAT TO KILL A DEMON.
( laughs )
- BUT, ON THE BOAT, YOU JUST
DISAPPEARED INTO THIN AIR.
- AAH!
- I REALLY HOPE
YOU KIDS CAN FORGIVE ME
FOR NOT TELLING YOU
THE TRUTH SOONER.
- HE CAN FLY?
- I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO DIDN'T
HAVE ANY MEMORY LOSS.
I HAD TO LEAVE,
'CAUSE EVERYONE WENT NUTS.
I KNEW I WAS A DEMON,
BUT EVERYBODY ELSE--
SUDDENLY, THEY THOUGHT
THEY WERE CURSED HUMANS!
( laughs )
- WHA--?
OH, BOBO!
( crying )
BOBO!
- I'M SO GLAD YOU FINALLY
SNAPPED OUT OF IT, POPS!
- ( all chattering excitedly )
- YOU'RE ALIVE!
- WE'VE GOT BOBO BACK!
- WE MISSED YOU!
- YEAH.
THEY ARE DEFINITELY DEMONS.
- I DON'T KNOW.
IF YOU LOOK AT THEIR FACES...
- MY SON IS ALIVE!
- ...THEY KINDA LOOK...
MORE LIKE ANGELS TO ME.
- HMM...
- ( chuckles )
- LET'S HAVE A FEAST TONIGHT
TO CELEBRATE!
IT'LL BE AN ALL-OUT DEMON PARTY!
- I DON'T KNOW IF I'M ROWDY
ENOUGH TO PARTY WITH DEMONS.
- ME EITHER.
- ( all chattering )
- THIS IS SO GOOD!
- ( all chattering excitedly )
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING? YOU'RE
SURE LOOKING A LOT BETTER.
- DO I KNOW YOU?
- MAYBE THIS'LL HELP.
- ( ticking )
- ( bell dings )
- I REMEMBER YOU.
- I LOOK A LITTLE DIFFERENT
NOW, HUH?
- UH, YEAH.
- JUST SO YOU KNOW,
EVERY GIRL IN OUR VILLAGE
HAS TOTALLY FALLEN FOR YOU,
'CAUSE WE THINK YOU'RE LIKE
THE COOLEST GUY EVER!
- YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT, WE THINK
YOU'RE SUPER AWESOME, GRAY.
- YOU PROBABLY THINK WE'RE CUTER
IN OUR HUMAN FORMS, DON'T YOU?
- NO, THAT'S NOT
NECESSARILY TRUE.
I THINK YOU LADIES LOOK FINE
THE WAY YOU ARE.
- Girls: AAH!
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE THE SWEETEST
GUY I'VE EVER MET.
- YOU KNOW JUST WHAT
TO SAY TO A GIRL.
- LET'S HIT THE DANCE FLOOR,
AND WE'LL TEACH YOU
THE DEMON WIGGLE-WAGGLE!
- ( Village girls chattering )
- OKAY.
- IT LOOKS LIKE
SOMEONE'S GETTING A LOT
OF ATTENTION FROM THE LADIES.
- HE'LL SCARE THEM OFF
SOONER OR LATER.
- WELL, I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I WAS WRONG ABOUT HUMANS.
- HUH?
- ALL OF THESE YEARS,
WE'VE CHOSEN TO HIDE
FROM THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
WE WERE SO AFRAID
THAT OTHERS
WOULD JUDGE US
BY OUR APPEARANCE.
- YOU KNOW THE CURSE?
THAT WAS JUST A RUMOR WE SPREAD
SO NO ONE WOULD COME TO
THE ISLAND AND BOTHER US.
- WELL, IT WORKED, 'CAUSE
THE SAILORS AT THE DOCK
WERE TERRIFIED.
NOBODY WANTED TO COME HERE.
- I KNOW,
AND IT'S A SHAME.
BUT AFTER MEETING YOU,
WE'VE CHANGED OUR MINDS.
YOU'VE RESTORED OUR FAITH
IN HUMANS,
AND NOW WE'RE NOT AFRAID.
WE'RE READY TO GO OUT
AND BEFRIEND PEOPLE
FROM OTHER LANDS.
- THAT'S GOOD.
FRIENDSHIP IS A BEAUTIFUL THING.
IT'S AN EMOTIONAL BOND
THAT TRANSCENDS
ONE'S PHYSICAL APPEARANCE.
- MM-HMM.
- ( chuckles )
- ( Villagers chattering )
- OHH.  ARE YOU REALLY
GONNA GO DOWN THERE?
- I HAVE NO CHOICE.
IT WOULDN'T BE RIGHT
TO LEAVE THINGS THE WAY
THEY ARE NOW.
YOU JUST STAY HERE
WITH COLD EMPEROR LYON, OKAY?
- ( growls )
- WE HAVE TO DO THIS.
IT'S ALL IN THE NAME OF LOVE.
- ( Villagers
chattering happily )
- UH-OH.
- HUH?
- OH, NO, NOT AGAIN.
- IT'S THE COLD EMPEROR'S
MINIONS.
- ( all murmuring )
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- DON'T WORRY,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF 'EM.
- ( gasps )
- HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- YOU FAIRY TAILERS ARE TOUGH.
THE COLD EMPEROR'S SO BANGED UP,
HE COULDN'T EVEN MAKE IT
DOWN HERE.
- THAT'S WHY WE'VE COME
TO PAY YOU A VISIT
IN HIS PLACE.
- WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
I THOUGHT WE WERE COOL.
DIDN'T LYON TELL YOU GUYS
WHAT HAPPENED?
- YES, BUT THAT DOESN'T
MATTER TO US.
- WE WANTED TO SETTLE THINGS
WITH YOU OURSELVES.
- ALL RIGHT, WHY DON'T YOU
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT?
- WAIT, NATSU!
THANKS FOR THE HELP,
BUT WE CAN'T KEEP
RELYING ON YOU,
SO LET US FIGHT 'EM.
- HE'S RIGHT.
WE GOT THESE CLOWNS.
- IF WE WANNA KEEP
OUR VILLAGE SAFE,
WE'VE GOTTA PROTECT IT.
- NORMALLY I WOULD
AGREE WITH YOU, GENTLEMEN.
BUT I THINK IT'S BEST
THAT I HANDLE THIS ONE.
- WE MEET AGAIN,
TITANIA OF FAIRY TAIL.
YOU GAVE DEAR ANGELICA
QUITE A BEATING EARLIER.
- SHE SEEMS LIKE
A FORMIDABLE OPPONENT.
- WATCH OUT FOR
THAT CREEPY CHICK!
SHE CAN CONTROL
INANIMATE OBJECTS.
- AND DON'T EVEN BOTHER
TRYING TO USE YOUR MAGIC
AGAINST OL' MEGABROWS.
- IS THAT SO?
IN THAT CASE,
I'LL DO IT
THE OLD-FASHIONED WAY!
HA!
- ( gasps )
- ( grunting )
- ( grunts )
- ( Villagers murmuring )
- HOLY...
- SHE DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
TO USE ANY MAGIC.
- THAT'S THE GREAT ERZA
FOR YA.
- WOULD YOU CUT THAT OUT?
- ( groaning )
YOU'RE TRULY
AN AMAZING WARRIOR.
- ( exhales )
NO KIDDING.
WE'RE NO MATCH FOR YOU.
- ( exhales )
- UH-- WAIT.
SO YOU'RE NOT HERE
TO ATTACK US?
- I DOUBT THIS IS
GOING TO MAKE UP
FOR ALL THE TROUBLE
WE'VE CAUSED YOU.
BUT WE WANTED TO
APOLOGIZE IN PERSON.
- OH, SO YOU GUYS CAME HERE
TO SETTLE THINGS IN A GOOD WAY.
- THE COLD EMPEROR
TOLD US EVERYTHING.
THANKS TO YOU, WE CAN
FINALLY LET GO OF THE PAIN
DELIORA CAUSED US
SO MANY YEARS AGO.
- YOU MEAN YOU WERE VICTIMS
OF DELIORA TOO?
- WHEN WE WERE CHILDREN,
THE MONSTER RAVAGED OUR VILLAGE.
WE WATCHED IT MURDER
ALL OF OUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
- THE COLD EMPEROR
HAD A PLAN
TO KILL THE DEMON
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
THAT'S WHY WE JOINED HIM.
- YOU SEE, WE WANTED REVENGE.
AND WE WERE SO FOCUSED
ON GETTING IT,
WE NEVER REALIZED
WE WERE HURTING INNOCENT PEOPLE.
- WE WERE SO BLINDED
BY OUR HATRED,
THAT WE ENDED UP ACTING
NO BETTER THAN THE DEMON ITSELF.
FROM NOW ON, WE'LL TREAT
OTHER PEOPLE WITH RESPECT.
AND LOVE.
- Natsu: ALL RIGHTY, THEN!
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
YOU GUYS SHOULD STICK AROUND,
AND JOIN IN ON THE FEAST!
HUH?
- BUT WE WERE ENEMIES
A SECOND AGO.
- I DON'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA,
BECAUSE I'M TRYING
TO WATCH MY FIGURE AND--
( gasps )
- ENOUGH WITH THE EXCUSES.
LIVE A LITTLE, WOULD YOU?!
OKAY, NOW I'M READY TO PARTY!
- ( all murmuring )
- WERE YOU ABLE TO SEE
ALL OF THAT, SIR?
- YES.  WHY DID YOU
RESTORE THE VILLAGE?
- 'CAUSE I'M NICE.
- SOME MIGHT SAY TOO NICE.
YOU'D BETTER LEAVE
BEFORE THEY FIND YOU.
THOSE FAIRY TAIL WIZARDS--
THEY COULD POSE QUITE A THREAT
WERE THEY TO GET IN OUR WAY.
- HEH.
( chuckles )
THAT'S TRUE.
- WHERE'D EYEBROWS
AND "LOVE" GIRL GO?
- LIKE TYPICAL PARTY GUESTS,
THEY STUFFED THEIR FACES
AND TOOK OFF.
- HMM...
I THINK IT'S GONNA
LEAVE A SCAR.
- WHATEVER, IT DOESN'T
MATTER TO ME.
- ON YOUR FACE?
- I DON'T MIND
HAVING A FEW SCARS,
AS LONG AS I CAN SEE 'EM.
IT'S THE ONES YOU CAN'T SEE
THAT STING.
- WELL, AREN'T YOU
A SMOOTH TALKER?
- SO YOU'VE GOT INVISIBLE SCARS?
- SHUT UP, NATSU!
EVERY TIME I SAY SOMETHING COOL,
YOU GOTTA RUIN IT!
- HOW WAS THAT COOL?
- WHAT?
BUT MISS, YOU DESERVE
THE REWARD,
SO TAKE IT.  PLEASE.
- THANK YOU.
BUT YOUR GRATITUDE
IS PAYMENT ENOUGH.
- THAT'S NICE, BUT YOU SHOULD
TAKE THE MONEY.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT
A FLAMING IDIOT LIKE YOU
WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
- I CAN'T BECAUSE YOUR REQUEST
WAS NEVER
OFFICIALLY ACCEPTED
BY THE GUILD.
IT FELL INTO THE HANDS OF
FOOLISH WIZARDS
TRYING TO PROVE THEMSELVES.
- ( laughs )
FOOLISH AS THEY MAY BE,
IF IT WASN'T FOR THEM,
WE NEVER WOULD HAVE BEEN SAVED.
WHAT IF I GIVE YOU THE MONEY
NOT AS A REWARD,
BUT INSTEAD
AS A THANK-YOU GIFT?
IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO
AFTER EVERYTHING
YOU'VE DONE FOR OUR VILLAGE.
- WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT WAY,
YOU MAKE IT HARD TO SAY NO.
- ( chuckles )
- SHE'S REALLY GONNA TAKE IT!
- WE'RE RICH!
I'M SORRY.
ACCEPTING YOUR REWARD
WOULD BE CONTRARY
TO OUR GUILD'S PRINCIPLES.
HOWEVER, WE'D BE HAPPY TO TAKE
THE GATE KEY YOU OFFERED
ALONG WITH IT.
- THE GATE KEY?!
- COME TO MAMA!
- WELL, AT LEAST LET ME TAKE YOU
BACK TO HARGEON.
- THANK YOU.
BUT I HAVE
A BOAT WAITING, SIR.
- HUH?
- A PIRATE SHIP?
- YOU KIDDING ME!
DID SHE HIJACK IT?!
- THIS IS AWESOME.
- AHOY, ME BEAUTY!
- ( all cheering )
- "ME BEAUTY"?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY'VE BECOME
QUITE FOND OF ME.
- THAT'S THE GREAT ERZA FOR YA!
- JEEZ, YOU'RE SUCH A SUCK-UP.
- AHOY!  COME ABOARD ME SHIP,
MATEYS!
- MATEYS?
- I DON'T WANNA!
I'M NOT RIDING
THAT CREEPY BOAT!
- IF YOU WANNA SWIM,
I'LL JOIN YOU.
- ARE YOU INSANE?!
- WEIGH ANCHOR!
WE'RE SHOVIN' OFF!
- Pirates: AYE AYE, SIR!
- ( Villagers chattering )
- WE THANK YOU!
HOPE YOU GUYS
WILL COME BACK SOMEDAY!
- YEAH, YOU BETCHA!
( laughs )
- SO LONG!
- Girl: HOPE WE GET TO DO
THE DEMON WIGGLE-WAGGLE AGAIN,
GRAY!
- GOOD LUCK BACK AT THE GUILD.
- FAIRY TAIL'S THE BEST!
- COME BACK AND SEE US
SOMETIME!
- YOU KNOW,
THEY WEREN'T SO BAD.
- GUYS, I'M NOT CRYING.
I GOT SOMETHING IN MY EYE.
- OH, YEAH?
YOU COULD HAVE FOOLED ME.
- ARE YOU OKAY, LYON?
YOU NEVER GOT THE CHANCE TO SAY
GOOD-BYE TO YOUR FRIEND.
AND GIVE HIM YOUR LOVE.
- IT'S FINE.
YOU TWO WERE IN A GUILD ONCE.
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
- IT'S QUITE A SHAME
THAT DELIORA DIDN'T WORK OUT.
- YES, IT IS UNFORTUNATE.
BUT WE HAD NO WAY OF KNOWING
THE DEMON WAS ALREADY DEAD.
C'EST LA VIE.
IT'S A RELATIVELY MINOR
SETBACK;
I'LL BE MORE THOROUGH
NEXT TIME.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
SIEGRAIN, SIR.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT WENCH'S
MAGIC WAS SO POWERFUL.
- YOU SHOULDN'T SPEAK ABOUT
YOUR MOTHER THAT WAY.
DON'T CAUSE UR
TO SHED ANOTHER TEAR.
SHE WAS A MAGNIFICENT WIZARD
WHO WAS GREATLY ADMIRED.
IN FACT, I THINK, IF SHE WERE
STILL ALIVE TODAY,
SHE WOULD BE COUNTED AMONG
THE TEN WIZARD SAINTS.
- YOU GIVE HER
FAR TOO MUCH CREDIT.
MY MOTHER LOVED HER MAGIC
AND NOTHING ELSE.
IT'S NO WONDER MY FATHER
ABANDONED THE WRETCH.
- THEY SAY THE GREATER THE LOSS
A PERSON SUFFERS,
THE STRONGER THEY MUST BECOME
TO TRIUMPH OVER IT.
- I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT MY MOTHER
EVER FELT I WAS A GREAT LOSS.
- HMM, YOU NEVER KNOW.
WHAT IF SHE TOOK ON
THOSE STUDENTS
TO FILL THE VOID
YOU LEFT BEHIND?
- COULD WE PLEASE
CHANGE THE SUBJECT?
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR US
TO MOVE ON TO THE NEXT STAGE.
- URTEAR, YOUR FACE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- WOW!
- THAT IDIOT NATSU PUNCHED ME!
- ( laughing )
THAT CERTAINLY IS
A DELAYED REACTION.
-SO HOW WAS HE?
DID YOU FIND HIM TO BE
A WORTHY OPPONENT?
- I NEVER HAD TO USE MORE THAN
HALF OF MY POWER AGAINST HIM.
BUT I WAS IMPRESSED.
IT SEEMS HE'S GETTING STRONGER
WITH EACH PASSING DAY.
- I'M NOT SURPRISED.
HE IS IGNEEL'S SON.
TO REALIZE MY DREAM, HE MUST
CONTINUE BURNING BRIGHTLY.
- WE'RE HOME!
- AYE, SIR!
- I'M BUMMED.
ALL THAT TIME AND HARD WORK
FOR SOME LOUSY GATE KEY.
- YEAH, AND THAT S-CLASS REWARD
WAS BIG TIME MONEY.
- WELL, I'M SORRY,
BUT IT WASN'T AN OFFICIAL JOB.
JUST BE GLAD YOU GOT SOMETHING.
- SHE'S GOT A POINT.
NOW QUIT YOUR COMPLAINING.
- THAT'S PRETTY EASY
FOR YOU TO SAY,
YOU GOT A REWARD!
CAN WE SELL IT?
- HOW COULD YOU
EVEN SUGGEST THAT, HAPPY?!
YOU GUYS JUST DON'T GET IT.
THEY'RE HARD TO COME BY.
SURE, THERE ARE LOTS OF
SILVER GATE KEYS,
BUT THERE ARE ONLY
TWELVE GOLD ZODIAC KEYS.
AND I'M LUCKY ENOUGH
TO HAVE FIVE.
- HMM, IT'S TOO BAD
THEY'RE ALL CRAZY.
- YOU HAD BETTER WATCH
YOUR MOUTH, YOU PUNK!
ME AND MY CELESTIAL SPIRITS
ARE GONNA BE STRONGER
THAN YOU SOMEDAY!
- SO, WHICH ONE OF THE ZODIAC
KEYS DID YOU END UP GETTING?
- IT'S SAGITTARIUS THE CENTAUR!
- IT'S A HORSE MAN?!
- WELL, YEAH,
BUT IT'S MORE LIKE THIS...
- YO, WHAT'S UP?
I'M SAGITTARIUS!
- AND THAT IS NOT
EVEN CLOSE, DUMMY.
- YOU'RE ALL SO CAREFREE.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
YOU FACE PUNISHMENT
WHEN WE GET BACK TO THE GUILD.
- ( all gasp )
- BUT WHY?
- EVERYTHING WORKED OUT
IN THE END!
CAN'T WE JUST FORGET
THE WHOLE PUNISHMENT THING?
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
EVERYTHING WORKED OUT.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE I CAME HERE
AND FINISHED THE JOB
NONE OF YOU WERE
QUALIFIED TO DO.
STEALING AN S-CLASS REQUEST
IS A SERIOUS OFFENSE.
- All: HUH?!
- WE SAID WE'RE SORRY.
- IF YOU PROMISE THAT
YOU'LL NEVER DO IT AGAIN,
THEN I DON'T THINK YOU NEED TO
BE PENALIZED BY THE GUILD.
UNFORTUNATELY, I DON'T HAVE
ANY SAY IN THE MATTER.
YOUR FATE IS IN
MASTER MAKAROV'S HANDS.
SO I'M SURE YOU'LL BE
FACING PUNISHMENT.
- NOW I'M SCARED.
YOU THINK HE'S GONNA
MAKE US DO THAT?
- JUST KILL ME NOW!
I DON'T THINK I COULD LIVE
THROUGH THAT AGAIN!
- YOU GUYS ARE FREAKING ME OUT!
- DON'T LET 'EM SCARE YOU.
I'LL TALK THE OLD MAN
OUTTA PUNISHING US.
THAT GUY LOVES ME.
- I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
SHOULD DO THE TALKING.
- NATSU...
YOU CAN'T TALK YOUR WAY
OUT OF THIS ONE.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
( chuckling )
- NO!  SAVE ME!
- ( Gray shuddering )
- Natsu: NOT THAT!
ANYTHING BUT THAT!
NO!
- WOULD SOMEBODY PLEASE
TELL ME WHAT "THAT" IS?
I'M TOTALLY FREAKING OUT!
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- PROFESSOR HAPPY'S CLASS
ABOUT FAIRY TAIL!
FOR TODAY'S LESSON,
I'LL TEACH YOU
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
OUR OTHER FAIRY TAIL MEMBERS.
OUR GUILD IS LED
BY MASTER MAKAROV,
AND SOMETIMES IT CAN
GET PRETTY CRAZY.
IT'S FULL OF
ALL KINDS OF WIZARDS
WHO PRACTICE DIFFERENT
TYPES OF MAGIC. YAY!
THEY FIGHT CONSTANTLY,
BUT DEEP DOWN
THEY'RE GOOD FRIENDS
WHO CARE ABOUT EACH OTHER.
WELL, THAT'S TODAY'S CLASS.
DISMISSED!  AYE!
- YOU'RE LUCKY.
I WISH I COULD FLY.
THINGS WOULD BE
SO MUCH EASIER.
- AYE. IT'D BE
AWESOME IF WE COULD
SOMEHOW SWAP MAGIC
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I'D LOVE TO BE ABLE
TO BREATHE FIRE LIKE YOU.
- YOU MAY BE ON TO SOMETHING.
YOU THINK THERE'S A SPELL
FOR THAT LYING AROUND?
- UH, I DON'T THINK WE HAVE
SPELLS JUST LYING AROUND.
- ( Happy and Natsu speaking )
- Happy: YOU KNOW,
I THINK THERE IS A SPELL
THAT ALLOWS WIZARDS
TO SWAP POWERS.
- ( Natsu laughs )
REALLY?!  COOL!
WHAT'S IT CALLED?
- STUPID SHORT-TERM MEMORY...