[gasps]
[IRENE]
So you've met my little ones.
In fact, it appears you had
quite a lively introduction.
[whimpering]
[MIRAJANE] Her magic power...
It's terrifying.
[MIRAJANE gasps]
[screams]
[screaming]
[IRENE] You will not
go gently into death.
Let me begin by taking that
flawless, beautiful skin
and tearing it into ribbons.
When I'm done, you'll be no more
than a lump of shredded meat,
unbearable to behold.
[MIRAJANE screaming]
[AUGUST]
Irene.
Can't control your extreme
proclivities, can you?
It's been a while since
we've crossed paths.
Nice to see you.
And you have Brandish in tow.
You've certainly grown.
[BRANDISH]
Yes.
Why did you cast Universe One
without the approval
of His Majesty?
[IRENE] I had been
confronted by Acnologia.
That was a battle I could
not risk being drawn into.
So I chose to expel
the Black Dragon
and send our Lord to
Fairy Tail all at once.
I don't believe this is
the time for lectures.
The Twelve are to assemble--
confer with him about
the way forward.
[IRENE] Sorry, but I believe
I'll do as I see fit, thank you.
That so?
You'll defy my order
as the appointed leader
of the Spriggan Twelve?
[MIRAJANE]
They both have so much power.
Can this even be real?
[IRENE]
Very well.
I suppose I've no choice
but to honor your request.
However, this girl
hurt my little ones,
so I simply can't let her live.
[gasps]
She won't be a bother
anymore. Are you satisfied?
A rather unexpectedly
compassionate move
from one known
as the "Calamity."
As you wish, then. Let's go.
I've missed you, big sister.
Yukino, I--
Whoa! What the--?!
I'm so confused!
Me, too!
I'm sorry, but I don't
have a little sister.
No! You do!
You're mistaken.
Must be someone else.
[YUKINO]
Sorano!
I'm not wrong.
I know it in my heart.
It's you! You're the one
I've been looking for!
They took you,
and I have done everything I
could think of to get you back.
I risked all I had.
I even went so far as trying
to turn back time for you.
Leave Yukino alone!
It's not her fault!
[YUKINO]
Sorano.
You were always there
to protect me.
You stood up for me,
and I never gave up hope
I'd see you again.
[ANGEL]
I told you, I'm not her.
How can you be so cruel now?
[ANGEL] There's no way a sinner
like me could be your sister!
My little sister is working
to make the world right.
She deserves better than someone
who's done so much wrong.
I pray... that maybe someday,
all of my horrible sins
can be forgiven.
And then, I'll
embrace my sister!
You'll be forgiven.
I know you will!
That's what I'm
fighting for right now!
But... I know I haven't
earned it yet.
It means so much to know
you're alive. I'm happy.
Oh. Ain't love a
beautiful thing?
She doesn't even know her.
It's okay if you
don't understand
all of the details, Frosch.
Yeah, I think so, too.
[ELFMAN] Mira. Lisanna.
Hope you're okay.
[LISANNA]
Mirajane!
I can't do it! I can't
leave you behind!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
Mira, hey! Mirajane,
please wake up!
Thank goodness.
[MIRAJANE]
The wound is shrinking.
[MIRAJANE gasps]
We gotta go, Lisanna!
They need us at the
guild hall, now!
That's where I was going.
Sorry. I came back.
Listen to me!
The Twelve are going there, too.
[WIZARD A]
Stop right there!
That's as far as
you're goin', lady!
Can't let a prisoner
like you get away.
The old hag would skin us
alive if we lost her.
[BOTH gasp]
What's happening? Oh my.
Ahh! It feels so good.
[BOTH gasping]
[LARCADE] May your spirits
white, into heaven take flight.
I have come for you, Dimaria.
I'm humbled.
Larcade Dragneel.
It's been so long
since I've seen you.
Feels like a hundred years ago.
Ninety-five, to be exact.
[ZEREF]
Nevertheless, the entire time
I could hear your voice
and sense your presence.
[MAVIS]
Here he is.
I have one last-ditch
strategy for defeating him.
First thing I needed
was my real body.
And now, I have it back.
However, there's one more
step that I have to take.
Another contradiction.
Can I even get my
mind around it?
[gasps]
[MAVIS]
No! I can't move!
That's not necessary, Invel.
Majesty, I am aware
of the relationship
you and she once had.
However, she is the
Fairy Heart itself.
Which means, she could
weaponize that power.
[ZEREF] Mavis understands
more than anyone
that the Fairy Heart
cannot be used.
Even if it would ensure
my long-awaited death.
The residual effects
would be catastrophic.
But still.
[ZEREF] Mavis had been
trapped inside that crystal
for a very long time--nearly
a century--completely immobile.
It pains me to see her
in such a state again.
So if you please.
Lord.
What now?
[INVEL] Then I'll leave
her body unfettered,
but her mind restrained.
[MAVIS]
What's happening to me?
It's like my thoughts
are all jumbled.
No! I need to stay focused!
Oh, honestly, Invel.
You worry far too much
for your own good.
[INVEL]
Part of my duty to the empire
is to ensure your
safety, Your Majesty.
[MAVIS] I can't hold
my thoughts together.
Is this his magic?
[ZEREF]
Mavis. Please come with me.
[MAVIS]
My body is moving on its own.
[ZEREF]
Look down there.
[gasps]
[MAVIS]
What's going on here?
Your friends are coming.
I mean, after all, you're
the heart of the guild,
and this hall their
beloved home.
However, will they be able to
survive the harsh journey?
I would love to see
the Fairies try!
I'll grind 'em into dust
before they ever get close.
How'd that work last time?
Not good, right?
Like you did any better!
But they won't get by me again.
'Course not.
Randi.
Mary.
Heard they captured you.
But it looks like
you're all right now.
Yeah.
[DIMARIA]
They'll pay for what they did.
Hear me? We'll slaughter
them together!
Friendship is lovely.
The sight of it warms me.
[grunts]
Not to be confused with the fire
of contempt I feel from you.
What else is he to do?
Follow his orders and
that may change.
[MAVIS] That old man is August,
the most powerful wizard of all.
But the other... His energy
feels different from the rest.
But I can't put
my finger on how.
So you've noticed Larcade,
my secret weapon.
The potential to defeat
Acnologia exists within him.
[sighs]
I must say, producing
Historias with the might
of the Spriggan Twelve
was no easy feat.
The "Eight Dragon" God Serena
has been resurrected!
You three are still dead.
But as long as I'm alive, you're
free to do what you please.
So it would behoove
you to protect me.
Let go! And just let god!
[IRENE] A million soldiers
plus the twelve of us.
What a sight to behold.
[ZEREF]
Irene.
[MAVIS] She's just as powerful
as the Wizard King.
[ZEREF] I'll pardon your
hasty use of Universe One.
In fact, I found it
worked to my benefit.
Oh, my.
In all candor,
I came here prepared
for a spanking
from Your Majesty.
However, I must ask for more.
A separation enchantment.
[IRENE]
Of course.
You need to remove the
Fairy Heart from this girl?
I mean, that is why we're here.
[gasps]
[MAVIS]
What? How is that possible?
Irene has a rare gift
for both imbuing magic
and taking it away.
[MAVIS]
No.
I imagine it'll be quite
a lengthy process.
[ZEREF]
Yes. Then proceed.
[MAVIS]
Is this it?
All our forces are gathered
and at the ready.
How far can your grit
drive you, Fairy Tail?
The truth is you will not
live through tomorrow.
Magnolia used to be
a town full of life.
And our guild was at its heart.
But those warm and
joyous days are gone.
[NATSU snoring]
I'll take all the fish.
So yummy.
Cherish those dreams.
And rest well.
[ERZA] Because this may be the
final dawn we face together.
We'll need our strength.
And each other.
[NATSU] The final one?
Not if I can help it.
It'll be tough.
But Fairy Tail isn't
gonna give up that easily.
Come on, let's go.
[NATSU] We'll bust in
and get our guild back.
[NATSU]
For the sake of our future.
For Fairy Tail.
We shall.
That's a whole lotta soldiers.
If we wanna get back home,
they're in the way.
We're gonna have to
fight our way through.
Sounds good to me.
It's obvious we're
heavily outnumbered,
so we can't charge in
headlong without a plan.
But what?
Come on! We'll have backup
before you even know it!
No way these jerks'll stop us!
Yes, you're right, Natsu.
Let's move forward.
When the others get here,
we'll push harder until
we reach the guild!
When we do, Master Mavis'll
be waiting for us.
So who's gonna beat
Zeref first, huh?
Let's make it a race, Natsu!
Yeah! Fire's in the belly!
[stomach growls]
Uh-oh.
Doesn't sound like there's
much in there to me.
You're a demon of
the Book of Zeref.
You'll die, too.
[NATSU grumbles]
[HAPPY]
There's gotta be another way!
No matter what, I swear
I won't let Natsu die!
Let's go!
Fairy Tail, here we come!
[SOLDIER A grunts]
[SOLDERS yelling]
Fire Dragon King...
Destruction Fist!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[TAURUS moos]
Ready, Taurus?
[yells]
--[TAURUS moos]
--[LUCY] Lucy Kick!
[JUVIA]
Water slicer!
[growls]
[GRAY]
Freeze Lance!
Requip!
[ERZA] Heaven's Wheel!
Scattered Petals!
[ERZA yells]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[SOLDIER D]
Are they really attacking us
with a handful of people?
[SOLDIER E]
They must be insane!
[SOLDIER F]
Get it together, men.
There's way more
of us than them!
Don't let 'em scare you!
[SOLDIER F]
Charge!
[WENDY]
Sorry we're late!
[NATSU]
Huh? Wendy!
Carla's here!
[WENDY]
Sky Dragon... Roar!
[rumbling]
[ELFMAN]
Beast Soul... Ape!
You're not alone Fairy Tail!
I'm here to help!
I suppose I could
lend a hand or two.
Hey, it's Elfman. Isn't it?
And it looks like he
brought some company!
Friendship sure is a beautiful
thing, ain't it, Frosch?
Yeah, I think so, too.
[FAIRY TAIL]
Charge!
[NATSU]
And there's our backup!
Oh yeah!
[gasps]
Look up in the sky!
They're dragons!
[GOD SERENA]
Ker-swoop!
[NATSU]
Huh?
This is as far as
you buffoons go!
Because the undead
version of God Serena
has made his godly descent!
[NATSU]
Uhh...
[GOD SERENA] Purgatory
Dragon Blazing Inferno!
Is that Fire Dragon
Slayer magic?
[NATSU]
Heh.
Time to chow down!
Ah. Well, if that's the case.
Sea King Dragon Water Vortex!
[choking]
He can use fire and water
magic at the same time?
So much power. How can
we fight him? With what?
All these elements!
Tempest Dragon.
Don't tell me he's
doing another one!
Just start swallowin'
everything! You hear me?
I can't eat it all!
That's him--Ishgar's
most powerful wizard!
[GOD SERENA]
Song of Moon and Wind!
[NATSU]
What the--?
Whoa.
[WIZARD D]
Uhh. Did we just get saved?
What happened? Who did that?
My spells disappeared.
Or more like... they shattered!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[chuckles]
Yo.
--It's Gildarts!
--[HAPPY laughs]
[BOTH chuckles]
I'm feelin' hungry.
I wanna go back to the guild
hall and have a snack.
[stomach growls]
[LUCY] Gildarts is back,
and he smashes a path
straight through to Fairy Tail.
But trying to follow
in his footsteps
is easier said than done.
Especially with the re-assembled
and re-animated Spriggan Twelve
vowing to stop us.
We're in danger of losing
the Fairy Heart for good,
along with Master Mavis.
Can we overcome the odds
and live to see another day?
Next Time: "The Winter Wizard."
Beneath the ice and snow
lies the promise of spring.