[colossal footsteps]
♪
[NATSU] Hey, guys...! It's time
for something special!
[KAIN] This is Kain,
and you're watching the
Sugary Sweet Mail Corner,
where I read your letters
and you watch me stuff my face.
Alrighty, then...
Our First letter...
"Could you please explain
Grimoire Heart's ultimate goal?"
Oh, well, uh... I guess
I can answer that...
Our official orders are
to capture Lord Zeref,
and to whip Fairy Tail
like a barrel of butter.
Our next writer asks...
"What type of girl is
Gray attracted to...?
Also, why isn't he
doing the post card segment?
'Cause he'd be
less of an eye sore."
Oh, yeah? Well, this is
my segment, so poo on you!
Are you taking me off the air?!
[HAPPY]
Back to our story!
Previously on Fairy Tail, Lucy
told Cana where to find Mavis'
grave and Cana thanked her
by knockin' her out cold!
What's goin' on here?!
Lucy Fire!
[KAIN]
Heave... Ho!
[LUCY] Hold on... Did
I miss something...?
Where'd the wrestler come from?!
Don't tell me this guy's
one of the Seven Kin?!
Cana...? Where'd she go?!
Where is my friend, dough boy?
[KAIN]
The ladies room maybe?
What have you done with her?
[KAIN] Listen, there's no reason
for you to be worried
about your little
friend right now.
Why...? Do you know
somethin' that I don't?
I know you're not gonna live
long enough to see her again.
[LUCY] Okay, I'm totally
confused. Was I sleeping
a minute ago?
How'd I lose track of Cana?
I hope she isn't dealing with
another one of these creeps.
I dunno what's goin' on... But I
need to take this guy down asap.
[KAIN]
Ya know glarin' at me like that
ain't gonna save ya...!
You might think it's
intimidating... but it's not.
Do you have any idea
who I am lady...?
I'm Kain Hikaru,
one of the deadly
Seven Kin of Purgatory...!
I'm super strong and stuff.
[LUCY] Strength doesn't
mean jack squat!
To a member of
Fairy Tail like me...
facing a strong opponent's
just another challenge...
I'll take you on...
and I'll defeat you.
First... answer one question.
I feel... something bristly on
my head, do you see anything?
[LUCY]
Are you talking about your hair?
Oh, great... Another weirdo.
Fine... You asked for it now...
Prepare to face my
Witching Hour Curse magic...
Ya shoulda run
while you had the chance!
[LUCY] Awkward and creepy...
What have I gotten myself into?
[childish laughter]
Before I destroy you,
do you mind giving me
a strand of your hair?
[LUCY]
Huh?
Come ooon... If you don't
give me a strand of your hair,
then I can't curse you
with my cursy doll.
[LUCY]
Yeah... Not happening.
[KAIN] All I need is one flimsy,
little strand, and Mr. Cursy
will let me control you
however I want.
You'll be pudding in my hands...
Mmm... pudding.
Tellin' me freaky stuff like
that isn't gonna help you
get your hands on my hair!
You're just realizing this now?!
Besides, everybody knows that
voodoo dolls are bogus...
You can't scare me
with a bluff, doughboy.
Huh...? That's not his name...
I already told you it's Mr.
Cursy; get it straight, lady...!
You don't have to be rude
just 'cause I wanna kill you.
[LUCY]
Uh, no...
I meant 'bluff' as
in an 'exaggeration'.
You know, like telling people
you're 'bloated' instead of fat.
Wait, are you calling me a liar?
'Cause that's even worse!
[LUCY] I think I just lit a
short fuse on a stick of stupid.
This guy is a total nut job!
If that's what you think,
then give it a try for yourself!
Wha...?! Are you
messin' with me?!
[KAIN] We'll use my bristle
for demonstration.
Just stick it on
Mr. Cursy's head, like this.
[NARRATOR] As you may have
guessed, when Kain refers to
his "bristle", he's talking
about his dry, frizzy hair.
He's ready!
[LUCY] I seriously hope this
creep doesn't reproduce.
Now go ahead and give it a try!
[KAIN]
There... See...!
Do you feel the power...?
You can apologize
to me anytime now...
Feel free to give him
plenty of hugs and kisses, too.
By the way, I'm startin' to get
hungry, so can we fight later?
Okay, that's enough, lady!
Hey... It's my turn now!
Break-dance spin...!
How about some yoga...?
That's right, feel the
burn...! You can do it, tubby!
[KAIN]
You witch! Gimme Mr. Cursy!
[LUCY]
What's the rush...?
There're still plenty
of embarrassing poses
we haven't tried yet.
Yeah baby...!
Like that...? Check it.
You're not supposed to enjoy it!
Ya know what?! Screw you!
All right... Now I'm angry...
And you can just forget
about asking me out on a date,
you hear me...?
I won't waste my feelings on a
bully who won't share her toys!
Trust me, I'll find
a way to get over it!
It's time for a non-stop ride on
the Kain Pain Train! Choo-choo!
Chugga-chugga-chugga-
chugga-chugga-chugga!
Sorry, but I'm putting
the brakes on this trip!
Don't run away from me...!
Why can't you accept
my feelings for you?!
[LUCY] I'll haveta fight big and
creepy with big and creepy!
Open...! Gate of
the Golden Bull!
Get him, Taurus!
[TAURUS]
Moo!
Celestial Spirit magic...
And an axe swinging moo-cow?
Listen up, Heifer...
The only bovine who's gonna
plough Miss Lucy's pasture
is the beefcake in front of ya.
Y'know, I haven't
had steak in a while.
Is it okay if I take a bite?
No, but you can kiss my
flank while I beat you!
Hey Taurus...!
Show this doll-lovin' sumo
reject we don't take any bull!
Then, how's about a peek
at that skirt steak?
[KAIN]
Dodoskoi!
How did chunky style
get the drop on you?!
I dunno... but I'm
tenderized... Smoooches.
[KAIN] My appetite's roaring and
I'm suddenly in the mood
for strip steak!
[LUCY]
Strip what?!
[KAIN]
Get back here!
[LUCY] What's with this guy?!
He's stronger without magic!
And how's someone his size
so light on his feet?!
His feet...?
Wait a minute... I got it!
Alright...! Open Gate of
the Archer! Sagittarius!
Yep...! Howdy-doo, my lady!
Horse meat?! Yummy!
[LUCY] Quick... Aim for his
stubby legs...! Trip him up!
[SAGITTARIUS] Righty-o! I'm not
letting you get your hands on
lady Lucy, or your
chopsticks on me!
[KAIN]
Dadastan!
He deflected them?!
No way!
I'm... beaten...!
Toodily-doo, my lady...!
[LUCY] Okay, now I'm angry...
Open, Gate of the Scorpion!
Scorpio!
Been awhile... but I'm
still wicked... Oh yeah!
Can we make this quick...?
Me and Aquarius are having our
own little island adventure...
and I'd hate to leave her
hanging ten... ya feel me?
By all means, get back
as fast as you can.
I don't wanna give her
any more reasons
to start plotting my demise.
Just cause you're on a trip with
your girlfriend doesn't mean
you gotta rub it in
my face...! Gah!
[SCORPIO]
Sand Buster!
I could go for a grilled
scorpion but I'd rather not
have all this sand!
Aw man...! That is wicked nasty!
So, uuuh... what now?
[KAIN]
Dodoskoi!
Hey Lucy... since my
sand ain't worth squat,
I'll be getting' back
to my bahama mama...
That cool? Wicked...!
So not cool! This blows.
I'm running out of spirits!
[KAIN] Mr. Cursy still has
my bristle on his head...
So what do you think
would happen if, say...
I could change what
his body is made of?
He's made cursing
himself an advantage?!
[KAIN] Change, Mr. Cursy...! I'm
gettin tired of being iron...
Let's go with light!
Shining Dodoskoi!
You can't defeat me, lady...
I may not look very tough,
but I'm still one
of the Seven Kin!
Better summon something tastier
before I really get mad!
[LUCY]
Well, he's not much of a fighter
but I bet he'll make
for a good distraction.
Open, gate of the Little Dog!
Nicola!
Oh, It's so cute,
I could just die...!
I just wanna pick him up
and hold him and squeeze him
and cuddle him and...
Gimme the yummy widdle thingy!
Guess my plan backfired!
Help me out here, Cancer!
Long time, no see... baby.
Holy crab legs!
What's the deal, you don't write
or call and your hair needs
a trim in the worst way...
Now, how's about we start
with some deep conditioning?
I see you're just as clueless as
ever... Go over and fight tubby.
[CANCER] Sorry baby but
I've got a fear of pots
and boiling water.
Well, get it over it 'cause
I need you to give him
a haircut so bad,
he'll run away in shame.
You got it, baby! Chop! Slice!
Like your haircut, baby?!
What...?! No way!
How did you wear down
my babies... baby?
My bristles haven't seen shampoo
since the stone age, pal.
[CANCER] That ain't
something to be proud of...
[CANCER]
Catcha ya later, baby!
'Kay... Only one shot left...
Get 'em, Aries!
I'll do my best...
You better have food for me...!
[ARIES] Sorry... I wish
I could satisfy you.
Wait a minute, why are you
apologizing to me?
[ARIES] Well, because...
You're starving...
and I can't do
anything to help you.
Sorry!
Please, don't go!
[IMAGINARY KAIN] My Darling...
I hate to see you cry...
Don't you know how
much I love you?
[ARIES]
You do?
Yes...! With all my heart!
[ARIES] Will you hold me
in your massive arms?
Are you kidding me...?!
Of course I will, dear!
[ARIES]
Kain, my love!
That's my, girl! Run into
my arms, sweetheart!
Aries... Thanks for filling my
life with wonderfully wooly joy.
I know we just met today...
but I love you!
Lay it on him.
Go! Wool Bomb!
I hope that I've properly
served you, Miss Lucy.
Yeah, you did great...!
I never knew you were such
a good actress; where'd
you learn how to do that?
Oh, Leo taught me!
Turn on the waterworks, and
men'll be putty in your hands.
Then you hit 'em with
a surprise attack!
Trust me, this trick'll
make you an asset to Lucy.
Yeah... remind me
to talk to him.
[KAIN] Why, Aries...?!
I know I can be clingy,
but why did you have
to break my heart?!
Dadastan!
I think we made him angry.
[LUCY] There's no stopping
this guy, is there?!
[KAIN]
Dodoskoi!
[ARIES]
I'm so sorry!
Fine, then... I'll have
to satisfy my hunger...
with a full-course dinner
of pain and suffering.
Mr. Cursy, change into cotton!
Last stop on the Kain Pain
Train! Self-reinforcement! Iron!
[HAPPY]
Natsu? Are you all right?
[NATSU] I'm fine.
Quit freakin' out, 'lil buddy...
Her hits ain't even hurtin' me.
[ULTEAR]
You're kidding yourself
if you think I'm going
all out right now...
I could have destroyed you,
but I owe you for Galuna Island
and I always make
good on my debts.
Whatever...
You're not any stronger
than you were last time.
Keep talking, little man...
It'll be that much sweeter
when I shut you up for good.
Look out below!
What the-?!
Natsu!
What the heck are
you doin' here?!
I don't need any help
taking her down!
I'm not offering...
But thanks for getting the
marshmallow off my back.
I can't believe you didn't see
her get a face-full of dirt...!
It was priceless!
You're gettin' a face-full of
my fist if you don't shut up!
Kain... care to tell me
what you're doing here?
Oh, yeah, sorry...
I was fightin' that girl and
I almost finished her off.
Looks like she's been
giving you a hard time, too.
I saw her first... Hands off.
You have fun with that.
[HAPPY] Natsu hasn't
landed a single hit!
There's no way he can beat her.
[NATSU] I can, too...! I was
just biding my time, ya know?
[HAPPY]
In that case,
I guess you can handle
the two of 'em on your own.
Yeah, I could, but since Lucy's
here I'll throw her a bone.
Now don't get me wrong,
we're still rivals when it comes
to completing the S-Class trial.
But... I don't mind
calling a truce for now.
[LUCY] Boy, teamin' up with you
guys sure brings back memories.
[HAPPY] Kinda reminds me of our
first adventure in Hargeon.
[NATSU]
I'm all fired up now!
Are you ready, Lucy?
You know it, Natsu!
Don't forget about me!
[KAIN]
Quit actin' all buddy-buddy!
It's driving me crazyyyy!
[KAIN]
My belly's rumblin'.
[LUCY] We're really taking
on two of them at once
I'm all fired up now!
That does it...! I'll
take care of these bratty kids;
just leave 'em to me...!
First I'm gonna filet
those two, and then...
I'll barbeque
their little, blue dog!
Forget it, Buddha belly!
We're stickin' with two-on-two!
Uh... Actually, I wouldn't mind
taking 'em on one at a time.
I'm not a dog, but at least
someone acknowledged me.
Very well, I leave them
to you... Destroy them...
I will take Zeref
to Master Hades so we
can continue our plans.
That's great news; I didn't
realize you had found him yet!
Oh no...! We have
to stop her...!
If she gets away with him
we're all screwed...
They wanna bring about
some "Grand Magic World"
and kill all non-wizards!
That sorry sack of tears
still has to pay
for messin' with my scarf...
He's not going anywhere
until I get my revenge!
Let's get this party started!
[KAIN]
Dodoskoi!
No, Natsu!
[ULTEAR] Kill them quickly...
We've no time to waste.
Show them the full fury
of the Seven Kin...
Head back to the ship as soon as
you're done decorating the
forest with their entrails.
No way...! I have a stomach
to fill and the main course
just got served...
There won't be any
leftovers to decorate with.
[NATSU] Bring it on!
I've got the porker, Lucy!
'Kay, guess that means
I'm goin' after her!
[KAIN]
Ka-shing!
[NATSU] Hey, What are you doin'?
She's gonna get away!
[LUCY] Look, I'm tryin' to move
but I can't seem to budge!
[childish laughter]
I snagged one of your bristles
while I was chasing you earlier.
But... How did you...?!
[KAIN] Now that you and
Mr. Cursy are connected,
it's time for me to serve
up your just desserts.
What was the first thing
you did to me...? Oh yeah!
Show us those funky moves!
[LUCY]
No!
Do you have any idea
what's goin' on here?
Just looks like a couple
of friends bustin' a move.
Oh, we've passed the 'friends'
stage at this point, doggie.
[LUCY]
Keep dreamin', bristle butt!
Aw, don't be so shy...!
You love to dance... and pose
for me, don't you...? Yes.
[LUCY]
Cut... It... Out!
Looks like you're
enjoying it, if you ask me.
No, it's all in your head!
For some reason, whenever diaper
man does something to that doll,
it happens to Lucy, too!
Whoa... That's cool.
[NARRATOR] Death curse magic...
this Lost Magic excels
at inflicting lethal
jinxes onto its victims.
The Lullaby flute,
created by Zeref, is another
example of a cursed object.
Even though Mr. Cursy doesn't
appear to effect more than
one target at a time,
in the right hands,
this terrifying magic could
re-shape the fate of the world.
Did you hear that...?!
We're totally screwed!
That's... not cool!
Hippity hoppity widdle wabbit.
C'mon, knock it off!
Make her tickle herself silly!
Hey...! Do you wanna die?!
I think that's exactly
what he should do!
[LUCY]
Natsu! Outta the way!
Are you copping a feel?!
[LUCY]
You deserved that one!
Wow, she's man handling
Natsu like Edolas Lucy...
And she wasn't
nearly that hard core!
What the heck
are you doing, Lucy?!
It's not me;
it's that creepy doll!
[NATSU]
That hurt.
Okay, this isn't
as fun as it looked.
Would you just stay still?!
Geez...! When did
you get so strong...?!
Either you've been doing extra
push-ups or that doll thing
is giving you a major boost.
Don't you two have any decency?!
Quit being cuddly and kissy
in the middle of a battlefield!
[BOTH] We're not doing
either of those, you perv!
Whatever, they're
totally in love.
[KAIN]
Now you got me steamed! Fine...!
You wanna get all handsy in
front of me...?! Take this!
I'll make you hug
your boyfriend so hard
his spine turns to jelly...!
There you go! Put the squeeze
on your main squeeze...!
Stretch him like
he's made of taffy!
This is just a taste
of the power of
Witching Hour Curse magic...
Your future is looking
very dark indeed.
Mr. Cursy...!
Why does everything I love
always run away from me?!
I managed to snag
the doll away,
what do you guys
want me to do with it?!
That stupid, blue dog can fly?!
Nice goin', Happy!
Awesome!
[LUCY]
You're so dead!
[KAIN]
That's my doll!
[NATSU]
It's mine now, bub!
Fire Dragon... Talon!
What gives...?!
How is he so fast?!
These Grimoire Heart
creeps are super strong...!
I never would've thought diaper
man could overpower Natsu!
Did you honestly think a wimpy
official guild could go toe
to toe with the
likes of us?! Dodoskoi!
Natsu!
[NATSU]
I'm stuck!
It's no good... I can't get out!
[LUCY] I'll summon Virgo
to help set you free!
No...
Not now... This is not the
time... to run outta power!
Lucy! Behind you!
Run away!
Leave her alone...! Come... on!
[KAIN]
Relax, little guy,
you've got a front row seat
to tonight's execution.
[NATSU]
You bastard!
Let her go! Take that, and that,
and that, and that, and that,
You'll join her on
the grill soon enough.
I gave it a shot...
but he's too strong...
Happy...
Get outta here, Lucy...!
You've gotta chase down that
broad or we'll lose her!
Don't worry about me, just keep
running and don't look back!
No way!
[LUCY] I refuse to run away...
I won't do it...
I'd rather stay here with you...
I can't think of anything
that would make me happier.
[KAIN] I guess that's one way
of saying goodbye...
I can't wait to pop that cute,
little head of yours off.
[NATSU]
You let go of her!
Careful... You'll break
my concentration...
I might not squeeze
enough the first time.
Whoa...! My body's
moving all by itself!
Dodge him, Lucy!
[LUCY]
Too far! That's way too far!
Available for
the first time ever,
it's the fully-poseable
Lucy action figure!
[LUCY] Did you forget
that I have joints?
Or are you trying to be
cruel and heartless?!
[NATSU] Quit complainin'!
You're beating him!
He's right...!
We might win after all!
Whoa... My pyro urges
are tingling like crazy!
[NATSU]
Fire Dragon... Iron Fist!
Chill out! This is gonna be
the greatest thing ever...
if you live!
Whaddya mean "if"?!
[NATSU]
Happy!
Aye!
Stop...! I don't wanna
play with you guys anymore!
It's time for Max Speed!
Aye, sir!
Okay... You guys suck!
[HAPPY]
Max Speed!
[KAIN] I gotta bad
feeling about this...
[LUCY] Screw you both! Next time
I get to set you guys on fire!
Special technique... Lucy fire!
[NARRATOR]
For those who didn't get that.
Using Mr. Cursy,
Natsu and Happy fused their
magic power with Lucy...
effectively turning her
into a comet of destruction,
and allowing her
to defeat Kain Hikaru.
Thanks... I've had enough...
I'm full now...
[NATSU]
He's down for the count!
[HAPPY]
Aye, sir!
We did it!
Now it's time... for...
A victory pose! Aw, yeah!
Guys... Haven't I been
through enough today?!
♪
[HAPPY] Sorry Natsu,
but I'm not gonna make it...
I can't move a muscle...
[NATSU] Pull yourself together,
Happy! You can't drop out of
a fight before you've
even done anything!
I mean, you can but
that'll make you a coward.
[HAPPY] Did you sharpen
that tongue before you
cut me with it?
I'm backin' off 'cause I've been
hoggin' the spotlight lately
and I wanna share it with you.
[NATSU]
Can't share what you don't have.
[BOTH]
Next time: Dead-End of Despair!
[HAPPY] Fine then!
I'll keep it all to myself!
I tried to be nice
but you've forced me
to go all Catmander on ya!
[NATSU] Oh no! What're you gonna
do? Cough a hairball on me?