- HEY GUYS! READY FOR SOME MORE
FAIRY TAIL? JUST MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING YOU TURN
THE LIGHTS ON IN THE ROOM,
AND DON'T SIT TOO CLOSE
TO THE TV!
( he laughs )
- OH MAN, HAPPY'S GONNA
FREAK WHEN HE SEES ME!
MAYBE I CAN SCARE
ERZA WHILE I'M AT IT!
WAIT. I KNOW LUCY'S TOTALLY
GONNA JUMP OUT OF HER SKIN,
IT'LL BE HILARIOUS!
- END OF THE ROAD FOR YOU, BOY.
- SOMETHING'S INTERFERING
WITH MY COMMUNICATION
WITH WALLY AND MILLIANA!
-I CAN'T EVEN TELL
WHERE THEY ARE NOW.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- HE'S TALKING ABOUT
TELEPATHIC COMMUNICATION.
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER, SHO?
- I'M FINE. EVERYTHING'S FINE
NOW THAT YOU'RE HERE.
- HEAVEN'S GAME!
- JUVIA, ARE YOU
ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN
THAT WE CAN TRUST THIS GUY?
I MEAN, I UNDERSTAND THAT
HE WASN'T ACTUALLY
TRYIN' TO KILL US BACK
AT THE RESORT, BUT STILL.
- I WON'T MAKE EXCUSES
FOR MY ACTIONS.
- I DIDN'T THINK
YOU COULD HEAR ME.
- ANY WIZARD WHO WAS INCAPABLE
OF SURVIVING THAT
WOULD NEVER HAVE
A PRAYER AGAINST JELLAL.
I NEVER DOUBTED THAT NATSU
COULD HANDLE THE ATTACK.
I WAS CONFIDENT
HE WOULD SURVIVE.
- OH YEAH, WELL WHAT ABOUT ME?
- NONE OF YOU CAN COMPREHEND
THE FULL EXTENT OF
NATSU'S ABILITY.
ONCE HE AWAKENS THE TRUE
DRAGON'S POWER WITHIN,
EVIL WILL FALL IN HIS WAKE!
- ( he sneezes )
- UGH! I CAN'T WIPE
MY FACE! GROSS!
I SHOULD PROBABLY TAKE
THIS OFF FOR A SEC.
COME ON YOU STUPID MASK!
- LET ME GIVE YA A HAND, PAL.
- WHAT THE--?
- NO!
- HEY, CUT IT OUT,
WOULD YA, MILLIANNA!
- IT'S THE BLOCKHEAD!
- WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
- YOU BIG OL MEANIE!
YOU WERE TRYING TO HURT
THE ITTY-BITTY-KITTY-WITTY!
- WAIT A SEC, THAT'S NOT EVEN A
REAL CAT, YOU CRAZY BROAD!
- MEOW!
- HE IS JUST THE CUTEST...
- A WISE GUY, EH?
- I'M TELLIN' YA DOLL,
THIS CAT IS A RAT, SEE?
- WHOA!
CAT MAKE BARRIER!
- NO, DON'T HURT
THE POOR KITTY!
- FOR CRYIN' OUT LOUD, DOLLFACE,
THIS DIRTY RAT IS OUR ENEMY.
MEOW!
- DIRTY RAT? IT LOOKS
LIKE A KITTY TO ME.
- IT'S A GUY IN A CAT COSTUME,
YA DIMWIT!
- MEOW!
- CAT FIRE!
DRAT! I GUESS JELLAL WASN'T
PULLING MY LEG WHEN HE TOLD ME
THIS CAT'S GOT SOME REAL CLAWS.
ALRIGHT, TOOTS. IT'S GO TIME!
- PRETENDING TO BE A CAT WHEN
YOU'RE REALLY JUST A PERSON
IS A LOUSY THING TO DO.
- OH YEAH? YOU'RE ONE TO TALK!
- BAD KITTY RESTRAINT TUBE!
- THAT'S GIVING HIM
THE BRACELETS THERE, DOLL!
- IT'S TIME TO PUT THE BAD
LITTLE KITTY TO SLEEP!
- HE'S IN THE BAG!
- CAT FIRE! HEY!
HOW COME I CAN'T USE MY MAGIC?
IS IT 'CAUSE OF THIS THING?
- FAKE KITTIES MAKE ME MAD!
- I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY,
SALAMANDER,
CAUSE YOU'RE ABOUT TA EAT LEAD.
- OH MAN, THIS IS NOT GOOD!
- EARS UP! I GOT A REAL DANDY
CATCHPHRASE I'VE BEEN
DYIN' TO TRY OUT.
TOO BAD THINGS
HADDA END DIS WAY.
BUT FROM THE MOMENT YOU MET ME--
- THAT YOU, HAPPY?
- YOU BETCHA!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE SAFE!
BUT WHAT'S UP WITH
THE CAT COSTUME?
- JUST GET THIS THING OFFA ME!
- AYE, SIR!
- LOOK PAL, NO ONE INTERRUPTS
WALLY AND LIVES TA TELL DA TALE!
- NO! I WON'T LET YOU HURT
THE WITTLE KITTY WITTY!
- CAT'S AIN'T NO FLYERS!
AND THEY AIN'T NO STINKIN
GUM FLAPPERS NEITHER!
- C'MON LIL BUDDY, UNTIE ME!
- AYE, SIR!
- EAT THIS!
- DON'T DO IT, WALLY!
- LEMME GO, YOU LOONY TOON!
- HURRY IT UP!
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME!
- I CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW
TO GET THIS STUPID THING LOOSE!
- CRAP! WELL, THEN I GUESS
I GOT NO OTHER CHOICE!
SPECIAL ATTACK!
SAD KITTY FACE! MEOW!
MEOW.
- WHOA! IT REALLY WORKED?
- WHY IN THE HELL D'YA
LET HIM GO YA DINGBAT?
- THE POOR WITTLE
KITTY LOOKED SO SAD.
- AW, FOR CRYIN OUT LOUD!
- I'M A FREE MAN!
- YEAH! GET 'EM NATSU!
- FIRE DRAGON WING ATTACK!
YOU MESS WITH THE KITTY!
YOU GET THE CLAWS!
- SO HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
WEAR THAT THING?
- 'TIL I CAN GET IT OFF.
( he chuckles )
- SHO AND SIMON HAVE
CHOSEN TO BETRAY ME.
AND IT APPEARS THAT WALLY AND
MILLIANNA HAVE FALLEN
AT THE HANDS OF SALAMANDER.
THIS IS HOW THE GAME SHOULD
BE PLAYED. ONE-SIDED MATCHES
ARE ALWAYS SO DREADFULLY BORING.
- BUT MASTER, ERZA MUST BE
CAPTURED AT ONCE
SO WE CAN BEGIN THE CEREMONY.
I'M AFRAID THE TIME FOR
PLAYING GAMES IS OVER NOW.
- PRUDENT AS ALWAYS,
VIDALDUS. FETCH HER.
- YOU'LL ALLOW ME?
- IT IS OUR TURN, AFTER ALL.
ASSASSINS FROM
THE DEATH'S HEAD ORDER.
VIDALDUS TAKA.
- GO TO HELL! YEAH,
THAT'S RIGHT!
THEY CAN SAY THEIR PRAYERS
IF THEY WANNA,
BUT THEY'RE ALL GONNA BE
BURNIN' IN HELL TONIGHT!
- FUKURO.
- ( hoots )
- AND THEIR LEADER, IKARUGA.
- LIFE IS A FLOWER.
FATED TO BE CUT DOWN AND
SCATTERED ON THE GROUND BELOW.
SO TONIGHT, WE MAKE MERRY.
WE ARE ASSASSINS HAILING FROM
THE DEATH'S HEAD ORDER GUILD.
THE SPECIAL FORCES SQUAD,
KNOWN AS TRINITY RAVEN,
IS AT YOUR SERVICE, SIR.
- IT'S TIME YOU ENTERED
THE FRAY. NOW, GO!
- HEY, HAPPY?
- YEAH, WHAT?
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
PULL HARDER THAN THAT!
- I'M PULLIN' AS HARD AS I CAN
BUT I CAN'T SEEM TO GET
THE STUPID THING TO BUDGE!
- IT FEELS LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA RIP MY HEAD OFF!
SWEET FREEDOM!
HEY LOOK, NOW IT'S STUCK
ON OL' BOXY!
- I'M AMAZED THAT
MASK WAS ABLE TO FIT
OVER HIS GIANT, SQUARE HEAD!
- THIS DANCE AIN'T OVER
YET, SALAMANDER!
- WELL, I ALREADY
GOT MY PAYBACK,
AND SINCE ERZA AND
HAPPY ARE SAFE,
THERE'S NO REASON FOR ME
TO KEEP WASTIN' MY TIME
WITH YOU, PAL.
- AYE, YOU TELL 'EM!
- TALK ALL YA WANT BUT WE'RE
STILL GONNA GET TA HEAVEN!
JELLAL TOLD US WE'D FINALLY
HAVE REAL FREEDOM--
--IN A WORLD WHERE PALOOKAS
LIKE US ARE CALLIN' THE SHOTS.
- I WELCOME YOU TO
THE TOWER OF HEAVEN.
AND THERE HE IS!
- MY NAME IS JELLAL AND I AM
THE RULER OF THIS TOWER.
I SEE THE PLAYERS
HAVE BEEN ARRANGED.
- SAY WHAT?
- SO HE KNOWS WE'RE HERE.
HE COULD BE LURKING ANYWHERE
IN THE TOWER, WAITING FOR US.
- I'M DELIGHTED YOU'VE COME
ALL THIS WAY TO SEE ME.
SHALL WE PLAY A ROUND
OF HEAVEN'S GAME?
- I DON'T WANNA
PLAY YOUR GAMES!
- WHADDAYA MEAN, JELLAL?
- THE RULES ARE
REALLY QUITE SIMPLE.
I WISH TO USE ERZA
AS A SACRIFICE
IN MY CEREMONY TO
RESURRECT LORD ZEREF.
- NO, I WON'T LET YOU.
- IF I SUCCEED, THE GATES OF
HEAVEN WILL OPEN,
CROWNING MY VICTORY.
- HOWEVER, IF YOU CAN MANAGE
TO FIND A WAY TO STOP ME,
YOU'LL BE THE WINNERS
OF THE GAME.
TO MAKE THINGS
A LITTLE MORE INTERESTING,
I'VE ENLISTED THREE KNIGHTS
TO BATTLE ON MY BEHALF.
- THREE KNIGHTS?
WHO COULD THEY BE?
- THE ONLY WAY YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO GET TO ME
IS IF YOU CAN DEFEAT THEM.
IN OTHER WORDS, A
THREE-ON-EIGHT BATTLE ROYALE.
AND THERE'S ONE MORE SURPRISE.
THE MAGIC COUNCIL HAS
THE SATELLITE SQUARE
FOCUSED DIRECTLY ON THIS TOWER
AND IT'S HIGHLY LIKELY
THEY WILL ATTACK.
AT THIS VERY MOMENT,
THEY'RE IN THE MIDST
OF VOTING ON WHETHER
THEY SHOULD FIRE
AN ETHERION BLAST.
- HEY, THAT WASN'T IN THE
DEAL, YOU HOODED FREAK!
IF THAT THING HITS US,
WE'LL ALL BE GOIN' TO HELL!
- NOW, NOW, VIDALDUS.
YOU WOULDN'T BE HAVING
SECOND THOUGHTS?
- NOT ON YOUR LIFE, BOSS!
FINALLY. HA!
THIS IS THE RUSH I'VE
BEEN LOOKIN' FOR!
A REAL DANGEROUS THRILL RIDE
TO GET MY BLOOD PUMPIN'!
- THERE'S NO TELLING
HOW MUCH TIME IS LEFT.
SHOULD THE ETHERION STRIKE,
COMPLETE ANNIHILATION
IS IMMINENT.
NO PLAYERS LEFT TO WIN;
GAME OVER.
- WHAT KINDA MESSED UP GAME
IS THIS?
- BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY
SENSE TO ME.
WHY WOULD THE MAGIC COUNCIL
RESORT TO SUCH DRASTIC MEASURES?
- ERZA!
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- NOW, THEN. LET THE GAME BEGIN.
- I WON'T LET HIM
LAY A FINGER ON HER!
- LET ME OUT OF HERE!
- I'LL BEAT JELLAL ALL BY
MYSELF IF I HAVE TO!
- NO! YOU CAN'T DO IT ALONE!
- ALL RIGHT,
NOW I'M ALL FIRED UP!
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GO TO
THE VERY TOP OF THE TOWER
TO FIND THIS JELLAL
GUY, AREN'T WE?
- BUT WHY WOULD HE
WANNA DO THIS TO US?
IF THEY REALLY FIRE THAT THING,
IT'S GONNA BE CURTAINS
FOR EVERYBODY.
WE WERE ALL JUST A BUNCH
OF STUPID KIDS LOOKING
FOR OUR OWN LITTLE
TASTE OF FREEDOM.
- I DUNNO WHAT KIND OF FREEDOM
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN LOOKIN FOR--
--BUT WHAT WE'VE GOT AT FAIRY
TAIL IS PRETTY AWESOME.
HEY HAPPY! I'M NOT FEELIN'
THIS GAME SO HOW ABOUT
WE BEND THE RULES?
- AYE, SIR!
- LET'S SKIP AHEAD
AND GO STRAIGHT
TO THE FINISH LINE, BUDDY!
- AYE SIR!
- HE'S A STAND-UP GUY.
AND THAT'S A DANDY
LOOKIN' SCARF!
SOMETHIN'S COMIN' THIS WAY.
WHAT IN THE WORLD WAS THAT?
- SALAMANDER IT'S YOU!
- HUH? WHO THE HECK'S
YELLIN' AT ME NOW?
- YOU'D BETTER WATCH
OUT FOR THIS GUY!
HE'S ONE OF THAT
BLOCKHEAD'S BUDDIES!
- OH YEAH? THAT MEANS HE'S
WITH THAT CREEP JELLAL!
- I'M NOT! TRUST
ME I'M ON YOUR SIDE!
THIS WHOLE TIME I'VE JUST
BEEN PRETENDING TO BE UNDER
THAT LUNATIC'S SPELL!
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
I'D BE ABLE TO STOP HIM!
- WE DON'T BELIEVE YOU!
- HOLD ON. IS THAT
REALLY THE TRUTH?
- YES.
- SO WHO IS THIS
JELLAL GUY ANYWAY?
AND WHY'S HE MAKIN' US PLAY
THIS RIDICULOUS GAME IN
THE FIRST PLACE?
- HE'S GOT A TWISTED
SENSE OF HUMOR.
HE'S THE TWIN BROTHER
OF SIEGRAIN,
A MEMBER OF THE
MAGIC COUNCIL.
I ASSUME THAT'S HOW HE
KNOWS THEY'RE PLANNING
TO FIRE THE ETHERION.
- SO THIS IS ALL JUST A FIGHT
BETWEEN TWO BROTHERS?
- IT'S POSSIBLE.
I DON'T KNOW THE SPECIFICS
OF THEIR RELATIONSHIP
OR WHETHER THEY ARE AT ODDS.
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
- I WILL NOT TOLERATE
THE BREAKING OF RULES!
NOW PREPARE YOURSELVES
TO BE PUNISHED
IN THE NAME OF JUSTICE!
FUKURO, THE KNIGHT OF TRUE
JUSTICE, HAS ARRIVED!
- A BIRD?
- YEAH, SOME KINDA WEIRD
JUSTICE BIRD!
- OH NO! DARK MOMENT!
- OH GREAT,
NOW I CAN'T EVEN SEE!
- I KNEW WE NEVER SHOULD HAVE
TRUSTED THAT GUY!
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THE OWL!
- HA!
- EVEN IN THE DARKNESS,
THE LIGHT OF JUSTICE
SHINES THROUGH!
HOO HO HOO!
YOU SEE?
- HEY MAN, ARE YOU DOIN' OKAY?
- THESE GUYS MEAN BUSINESS.
THEY'RE ASSASSINS FROM
THE DEATH'S HEAD ORDER!
- ASSASSINS HAVE GUILDS, TOO?
- THEY BELONG TO ONE
OF THE DARK GUILDS.
THEY REFUSE TO TAKE
ON REGULAR JOBS.
THEY MAKE THEIR LIVING BY
ACCEPTING REQUESTS THAT INVOLVE
USING THEIR MAGIC
TO TAKE LIVES FOR MONEY.
THE WIZARDS WE'RE UP AGAINST
ARE KNOWN AS TRINITY RAVEN.
THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR KILLING
EVERY SINGLE OFFICER
IN THE WESTERN ARMY
DURING THE CABRIA WAR.
THEIR POWER IS LEGENDARY.
- SO YOU'RE TELLING
US THAT BIRDBRAIN HERE
IS ACTUALLY SOME
KIND OF SUPER KILLER?
- HOO HOO HOO! AND IF
YOU'RE EVIL, WE'LL KILL YOU!
- THEY ARE PROFESSIONAL
ASSASSINS!
YOU CANNOT DEFEAT THEM!
- NOW SALAMANDER.
WORD BACK AT OUR GUILD
IS THAT YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR MANY EVIL DEEDS.
IT'S MY DUTY AS A
KNIGHT OF JUSTICE
TO SEE THAT YOU ARE PUNISHED!
- MAGIC GUILDS ARE SUPPOSED
TO BRING LIKE-MINDED
PEOPLE TOGETHER
SO THEY CAN SHARE THEIR DREAMS.
THEY'RE NOT PLACES FOR
KILLERS LIKE YOU TO TEAM UP!
- DON'T DO IT, SALAMANDER!
I'M TELLING YOU,
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN BEAT HIM!
- I HATE IT THAT THERE
ARE PEOPLE OUT THERE
WHO WILL PAY SOMEONE
TO COMMIT MURDER!
I HATE THAT THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO WILL KILL FOR MONEY.
AND I HATE THAT YOU'RE TALKING
LIKE YOU'RE IN A REAL GUILD.
SO I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TAKE YOU DOWN A NOTCH!
HEAR ME BIRDBRAIN? LET'S DANCE!
- OH LITTLE SALAMANDER,
YOU ARE STILL SO NAIVE.
I'M DOING THIS WORLD A
GREAT SERVICE BY DESTROYING
THOSE WHO COMMIT EVIL
DEEDS. THRUSTERS!
AND SINCE YOU ARE AN EVILDOER!
YOU MUST BE DESTROYED!
JET! HOO!
- NATSU!
- YOU THINK YOU CAN
FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE?
AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN,
YA DODO BIRD!
- HOO HOO!
ONCE MORE! THRUSTERS!
THROW!
- NATSU!
- NOW THAT HURT.
- IMPRESSIVE.
YOU'RE A LOT STRONGER
THAN I EXPECTED YOU TO BE!
THIS JOB MAY ACTUALLY PROVE
TO BE REAL CHALLENGE FOR ONCE!
- I KNEW THEY'D BE TOUGH TO
BE BEAT BUT I HAD NO IDEA.
AND THERE ARE STILL
TWO MORE MEMBERS.
- SHAME ON YOU, SIMON.
DEFEATED SO EASILY AT
THE START OF THE GAME.
OUR NEXT MATCH IS FUKURO
VERSUS NATSU DRAGNEEL.
I WAS VERY MUCH LOOKING
FORWARD TO FACING HIM MYSELF.
BUT THE ODDS DO
NOT LOOK PROMISING.
- NATSU?
- SALAMANDER!
- NATSU? AW MAN.
HE'S GOT EARS LIKE A DOG,
SO HE SHOULD BE ABLE TO HEAR US
CALLING NO MATTER WHERE HE IS.
- AH, THEN HE'S JUST LIKE GAJEY.
DOES HE HAVE A
KEEN NOSE AS WELL?
- GAJEY, HUH?
- I CAN'T IMAGINE WHY I WAS
CHOSEN TO SEARCH ALONGSIDE
THIS BLONDE BIMBO
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- GIMME A BREAK. IT'S NOT LIKE
I WANNA WORK WITH YOU EITHER.
- I'M GONNA RESCUE
ERZA FROM SHO.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU
LADIES TO FIND NATSU.
PLEASE DON'T LET ME DOWN,
MY DEAREST JUVIA.
- I'LL GLADLY DO ANYTHING MY
BELOVED GRAY ASKS OF ME,
BUT DOESN'T
HE REALIZE
THAT LEAVING TWO ROMANTIC
RIVALS ALONE TOGETHER
IS A RECIPE FOR A BLOODBATH?
- I'VE TOLD YOU A HUNDRED TIMES,
I HAVE NO INTEREST IN HIM--
NOW CAN WE DROP THIS
AND START LOOKIN' FOR NATSU?
( loud and shrill sound )
WHAT IS MAKING THAT
AWFUL NOISE? IS IT A GUITAR?
IT'S SO LOUD!
- I ACTUALLY THINK IT SOUNDS
PRETTY COOL.
- YOU HAVE GOT SOME
MAJOR ISSUES, GIRL.
- YOU BABES DIG
MY DESTRUCTION SOLO?
CHECK OUT THE HAIR!
- I'M AN ASSASSIN WITH
THE DEATH'S HEAD ORDER!
PRETTY ROCKIN' NAME, HUH?
A "DEATH HEAD" IS
LIKE A SKULL, GET IT?
- I TAKE IT YOU'RE ONE OF THE
THREE KNIGHTS JELLAL SPOKE OF?
- I'M A WING OF
THE TRINITY RAVEN!
WHEN THEY SCREAM "VIDALDUS TAKA"
THEY'RE TALKIN' ABOUT ME!
ROCK YOU!
WHOA, THAT'S ONE CRAZY
BODY YOU GOT THERE! HEH.
- IT'S MADE ENTIRELY OF WATER.
DRIP, DRIP, DROP.
- ALRIGHT JUVIA!
IT'S UP TO YOU!
- YOUR ATTACKS WILL HAVE NO
EFFECT ON ME WHATSOEVER.
WATER LOCK!
- WHAT'S THAT? DID YOU JUST
SAY YOU WANNA ROCK?
- IS THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
- YOU ELEMENT FOUR
PEOPLE ARE SCARY.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE
ON OUR SIDE NOW!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND-- MY WATER
LOCK JUST DISAPPEARED!
- WHERE'D ALL THAT WATER GO?
- SOMETIMES IT'S BEST TO JUST
GIVE YOUR LOCKS A GOOD RINSE.
SHAMPOOING EVERYDAY CAN
REALLY DRY OUT YOUR HAIR.
- BUT HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO
BREAK FREE FROM MY WATER LOCK?
- IT WAS EASY 'CAUSE MY ROCK
STAR HAIR ABSORBS LIQUIDS.
JUST AS LONG AS IT AIN'T OIL
OR ALCOHOL, YA KNOW?
THAT STUFF'LL REALLY
MESS UP YOUR 'DO.
- WATER HAS NO EFFECT ON HIM?
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
- MAN I GOTTA TELL YA, BOTH OF
YOU LADIES ARE HOTTER THAN HELL.
- OH HERE WE GO AGAIN!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- I SWEAR, BEING THIS CUTE CAN
BE A REAL CURSE SOMETIMES.
- EENY, MEENY, MINEEY, MOE,
OH NO!
I JUST GOT TO CATCH ONE OF
THESE HOT CHICKS BY THE TOE!
YOU'RE IT, BABE! I'M GONNA MAKE
YOU MY SUCCUBUS!
- YOUR SUCCUBUS?
- ROCK OF SUCCUBUS! OH YEAH!
- WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
OH, YEAH!
- NO! LEAVE ME ALONE!
- JUVIA! WHAT'S GOING ON?
- STAY BACK! HE'S TOO DANGEROUS!
- AND SO FALLS THE RAIN WOMAN.
I WONDER WHAT'LL HAPPEN NEXT.
- HEY JUVIA?
- SHE'S MY SLAVE NOW, BABE.
- I'M GONNA TAKE YOU FOR A
RIDE STRAIGHT TO HELL, BLONDIE!
SAY YOUR PRAYERS IF YOU WANNA,
BUT YOU'LL STILL BURN
IN HELL TONIGHT!
- WHAT DID THAT GUY DO TO HER?
- LOOKS LIKE THIS IS THE END
FOR THE CELESTIAL WIZARD.
- I HEARD THAT WHEN ERZA WAS A
LITTLE KID, SHE WAS REALLY SHY,
AND WOULDN'T EVEN LET
ANYONE COME NEAR HER.
- THAT'S KINDA HARD
TO IMAGINE NOW.
- I BETCHA SHE JUST ACTS TOUGH
'CAUSE SHE'S TRYIN'
TO PROTECT HERSELF
FROM THE PAINFUL STUFF SHE WENT
THROUGH WHEN SHE WAS YOUNG.
- SHE HAS ALL THAT ARMOR
TO PROTECT HER, THOUGH.
- NO, I MEAN SHE KEEPS
HER HEART CLOSED
SO SHE DOESN'T GET HURT AGAIN.
Both together: NEXT TIME:
ARMOR OF THE HEART!
- UH, SORRY PAL,
BUT I THINK YOU'RE GETTIN'
A LITTLE TOO DEEP FOR ME.
- BUT YOU'RE ALWAYS
WIDE OPEN, NATSU!
- DID YOU SAY "OVEN"?
I'M STARVING RIGHT NOW!