[GRAN DOMA]
Whatever the truth,
we've put off this
problem for too long.
It's time we dealt with it.
We don't know as
much as I would like.
But, if we can crush Tartaros,
the Baram Alliance will
certainly disappear.
I propose that we employ
the full power of the Council
to remove this blight
from the face of Fiore.
[SID, NOCRA]
Uh...
[LEIJI]
Mm...
[ORG grunts]
There's an emergency situation!
[LEIJI]
Hm?
What's the fuss about?
You fool! This better
be important!
[MESSENGER 234A] I'm terribly
sorry. But, there's an intruder!
[ORG]
Uh!
[FROGS scream]
[DORANBOLT]
Master Org!
We're not out of danger!
--[ORG groans]
--[DORANBOLT] Uh!
[JACKAL]
You can't be alive.
Killing all of you
was the whole point.
Your pals played along, but I
guess you need some convincing.
Explosion.
Damn you!
[ORG]
Doranbolt. Run away!
[DORANBOLT grunting]
I can't do that!
There's no reason for you
to die with the rest of us.
Hate to burst your bubble,
but there's no running
from my explosions.
[ORG]
Leave! Do it now!
[DORANBOLT groaning]
The name's Jackal, by the way.
One of the Nine Demon
Gates of Tartaros.
Tell that to your
friends in hell.
They should know the name of
the man who slaughtered them.
Tell them I enjoyed it.
[ORG groaning]
Live!
Find what justice means to you,
and defend it till the end.
That's an order!
[chuckles]
[DORANBOLT]
Master Org!
[CROWD screams]
[COBRA] No one in
Tartaros is remotely human.
They're all demons,
from the Book of Zeref.
[DORANBOLT gulps]
[COBRA]
Their master's name is. E.N.D.
The most powerful demon
there's ever been.
Whirr.
[YAJIMA whimpers]
What is this guy?
Yajima, no!
[BIXLOW, FRIED grunt]
[BIXLOW groans]
[FRIED groans]
Ka-boom!
[BIXLOW screams]
[FRIED screams]
[YAJIMA groans]
Fwoosh.
[YAJIMA screaming]
Today we go to war!
Our foe is a pillar of
the Baram Alliance.
As strong as Grimoire heart
and the Oración Seis.
But they should've learned
from their allies' mistakes!
For by the time
our work is done,
the bloodied remnants
of their guild
will look back on
this day and rue it!
For this is the day they
made an enemy of Fairy Tail.
They've attacked our brethren.
The pain they've caused
is mine and yours.
The blood they've
spilt is our blood.
Now it is time for the
blood not shed to boil.
For our pain to feed
our burning rage.
Let us fight not for justice,
but for the thunder
in our souls.
I make this oath upon
the honor of our guild.
Fairy Tail will
destroy this foe!
[FAIRY TAIL MEMBERS cheer]
[JACKAL] But you should
learn to pay attention
when someone's talkin'.
Huh?
Natsu! Look!
[NATSU]
Uh! What the...?
My curses can change anyone
stupid enough to touch
me into a living bomb.
I wonder. How many
times did you touch me?
[NATSU growling]
Are you okay?
Keep away, Happy! That goes
for the rest of ya, too!
[LUCY]
But, Natsu.
[WENDY]
We can't!
Get outta here!
[WENDY, LUCY, HAPPY panting]
--[CARLA screams]
--Natsu!
[LUCY]
Get down!
[laughing]
[MICHELIA]
Oh no!
Is he...?
I can't really tell.
[JACKAL] We don't use
magic in Tartaros...
[NARRATOR] After learning of
Tartaros' plan to eliminate
both current and former members
of the Magic Council,
Fairy Tail dispatched several
teams to thwart them.
They sent their strongest
wizards to the home
of each former council
member they could locate.
[CARLA, HAPPY]
Uh...
[JACKAL]
Explosion Spiral!
[WENDY, LUCY scream]
[WENDY screams]
[LUCY groans]
[WENDY groans]
[HAPPY]
This is bad!
[CARLA]
No, Wendy!
[WENDY, LUCY whimpering]
[NARRATOR] Sent along with Lucy
and Wendy to protect Michello,
Natsu began a hard battle
with Jackal of Tartaros.
[NATSU] I've already
gotten the hang of it.
[JACKAL]
Say what?
Natsu!
Be careful!
[JACKAL gasps]
[laughs]
[CARLA, HAPPY laugh]
[WENDY, LUCY laugh]
This shouldn't be possible.
How are you standing?
What did you do?!
You got me all fired up.
I don't get it.
Just who are you?
[NATSU]
I'm Natsu!
[JACKAL groans]
[chuckles]
Idiot. Ha! You touched me again.
Ya know what that means.
It's time for you to go nova!
Natsu!
Hang in there!
[JACKAL laughs]
[JACKAL grunts]
[NATSU] That was pretty
nasty the first time.
But now I know what to expect.
[JACKAL]
No matter what I try...
[JACKAL] ...this human
just consumes my curses.
He might be even stronger than
he was when this fight started.
I was wrong. There's
no way he's human.
He's a monster!
[JACKAL groaning]
--[JACKAL groaning]
--[NATSU] Uh.
[JACKAL]
But so am I!
Guess he's not surrendering.
Watch out! We don't know
what he can do in this form!
Uh?
[JACKAL roars]
[roaring continues]
Least now we know where
he got his name.
[JACKAL roaring]
[JACKAL roars]
[NATSU grunts]
--[JACKAL roars]
--[NATSU groans]
[LUCY, WENDY scream]
[NATSU groans]
[JACKAL roars]
Punchin' walls, are ya?
Leave the town outta this,
your fight's with me.
[JACKAL]
I'm a demon.
The most perfect and
powerful creature there is.
Humans are like cockroaches
to my kind. Easy to kill!
You're a demon?
I hope I didn't hear that right.
You the only one, or is
your guild full of demons?
I'm done talkin'!
I came to spill some blood!
If that's the only thing
you're fightin' for,
then you never stood a chance!
[JACKAL roars]
[NATSU] 'Cause we're
fighting for our friends!
The ones your guild-mate
tried, and failed, to kill!
[JACKAL groans]
[NATSU] I don't care you're
a human, god, or demon.
You hurt my friends,
you pay the price!
This one's for Laxus,
and the Thunder Legion!
Lightning Flame Dragon.
Firing Hammer!
[JACKAL screams]
[NATSU panting]
Bad guy's down.
Town's destroyed.
I'd say our work here is done.
That's how we roll.
[WENDY, LUCY]
Uh?!
Natsu!
That explosion was huge. Even
for someone as tough as him.
[HAPPY]
What happened? You okay?
We managed to evacuate the
townspeople to a safe distance!
[HAPPY]
Uh... Natsu!
What did we miss?
Turns out Jackal was a demon.
Natsu managed to beat
him, but just barely.
[NATSU]
Yup. Kicked his butt.
We're very proud of you.
--[NATSU groans]
--Wore yourself out hittin' him?
He has quite a bit
to answer for.
[JACKAL laughs]
[WENDY, LUCY, HAPPY gasp]
Well. I'll be damned
if I saw this comin'.
Haven't taken a beating like
that since I was still a pup.
Guess it had to happen sometime.
Kyoka, forgive me.
[JACKAL] You're gonna have a
tough time bringin' me back.
But this is the only one way
to take these humans with me.
Guys? I don't like this.
Me neither.
He must be planning to
demolish the whole town.
[LUCY]
Stop! Please!
Even if I wanted to,
it's too late.
I'm not the kinda bomb
that you can just defuse.
This body is rigged to
blow, even if it dies.
[laughs] I'll see you in hell,
so don't miss me too much!
What do we do now? We're gonna
get caught up in the blast.
[HAPPY grunts]
[HAPPY]
Not if I can help it!
[screams]
Hey!
Happy! No!
What're you...
You stupid little cat!
Happy! Get away from him, now!
You can tell your
friends to stay in hell,
'cause you're
never gonna win!
[JACKAL]
I'll be back!
Happy!
[LUCY whimpers]
[WENDY whimpers]
[CARLA cries]
This can't be for real.
[NATSU]
He can't be gone.
[NATSU gasps]
[CARLA gasps]
[WENDY, LUCY, NATSU laugh]
Nice hair.
I could really use a fish.
We're gettin' close to town.
Hope we're in time.
[JUVIA gasps]
Easy... What's the matter?
[creature growling]
I think she must be
frightened of something.
[GRAY]
Uh.
Who knows what's waiting for us.
You've found Master Hogg?
[GRAY] We did, but Tartaros
found him first.
Just how late were we?
Has the culprit left?
[JUVIA]
Late enough, and yes,
the killer is gone
but, unfortunately,
not without a trace.
[GRAY] They destroyed half
the town on their way out.
Such horrific destruction.
How was your luck, Gajeel?
What's Master Belno's
current status?
[GAJEEL]
They murdered her, too.
The city's fine though, nothing
like what Gray described.
It would seem that this
killer is the stealthy type.
[GAJEEL] I failed.
I should've gotten here sooner.
We did our best.
They beat us to Master Hogg
and Master Belno, so,
that leaves us with
Master Michello,
who we assigned to Natsu's team.
And Master Yuri, who Elfman and
Lisanna have been searching for.
We didn't make it. Can't tell
how, but they got him.
What do we do now?
Get the communication
lacrima ready.
We need to report
this to the guild.
[LISANNA]
Right.
[ELFMAN] I don't understand it.
He's completely uninjured.
It's almost like
he died naturally.
[gasps]
[LISANNA]
Uh?!
Master Yuri, you're alive. I
checked your pulse, and...
[yelps]
What do you think you're doing?
That was our only way
of reaching the guild!
[LISANNA, ELFMAN]
Uh...
Uh. Did he just
die all over?
That was creepy.
[SEILAH] I did try to make
him look convincing,
but a corpse is a corpse.
[sighs]
Are you from Tartaros?
Tell us what you did
to Master Yuri, now!
The old man already had
one leg in the netherworld,
I merely helped him along.
And stayed to play
with his corpse?
These Fairy tales are quite
dull. They all end so happily.
About as entertaining
as watching blood dry.
What your kind needs
is a demon tale.
Lisanna. Are ya ready?
Yeah!
Uh... Uh!
Hey, what are you
doing, brother?
[LISANNA choking]
[ELFMAN] This isn't me.
I'm sorry, I-I can't control it!
Lisanna, no! Please,
hang in there!
Elfman, you have
to tell the guild.
[ELFMAN] Whatever you're doing
to me, stop! Stop it right now!
One thing I prefer
about demon's tales,
they don't contain irksome
words such as mercy.
It's working! Hey, gramps,
can you hear me?
[MAKAROV]
Lucy? What happened?
We'd've contacted you
sooner if we could,
but we ran into a little
trouble on the mission.
Have you located Michello?
[LUCY] Yeah, he's
safe and sound.
[ALL]
Ah!
Can't quite say the
same for Natsu though.
I'm the champ.
He beat a member of
Tartaros all by himself!
Victory!
And he's proud of it.
The town looks like a
hurricane's been through it.
You could say that
about my hair, too.
We need to know everything
you were able to find
out from Michello.
About that...
They seek The White Legacy.
They will use Face.
[MICHELLO whimpers] Believe me.
I know nothing, I swear!
I don't know anything,
I'm telling you!
What is this "Face"?
It's a weapon.
The most powerful
one the council has.
Probably the strongest
ever made.
[MAKAROV]
Mm.
[GRAY, JUVIA]
Uh.
[GAJEEL, LEVY]
Huh?!
[WENDY]
Uh...
[NATSU grunts]
What was it for?
Somethin' like that sounds
too strong to use.
I'm sure they thought they
needed one last ace in the hole.
Power breeds paranoia,
from what I've seen.
Now I for one would
love to hear more.
The council possesses
many such weapons.
Each subject to its own rules,
based on its potential
for misuse.
One example is the
Etherion Cannon.
[MICHELLO] Etherion is a
hyper-magical artillery piece,
capable of dropping its ordnance
at any target in the continent.
It has power enough to
turn an entire nation
into a smoking crater
with a single blast.
Thus it cannot be fired
without the approval of nine
Council members and the
input of ten security codes,
each possessed by a
different senior official.
Wait a sec... All of those
council members are dead now.
Then the council can't
activate Etherion,
till they get new leaders.
They may have killed current
members to shut it down,
and retirees to keep it down.
[MAKAROV] What exactly does
this "Face" of yours do?
I understand that this is a
secret, but no one's left
to make use of your
knowledge but us.
Face is an anti-magic
pulse bomb. This device
can clear our continent
of any trace of magic.
Uh!
A weapon that can
erase all magic?
That's horrible!
[CARLA whimpering]
That would give Magic
Deficiency Syndrome
to every wizard alive.
It gets even worse.
The demon that Natsu fought,
told us that Tartaros members
use curses instead of magic.
So Face's activation would wipe
out every guild but theirs.
Every wizard who
stands against them
would find themselves
helpless and in agony.
What a deplorable weapon
your council has made.
[MICHELLO whimpers]
You tell me where
it is right now.
That thing never should've
existed in the first place.
I... I really don't know.
Please forgive me.
From what I heard,
it was sealed away by three
former council members.
They did this by means
of body link magic.
I have no idea who
those members are.
Only the former chairman
can tell you that.
So what the heck is
body link magic?
It's the kind that Brain used
to keep Zero sealed away.
If us beatin' the Seis broke
the seals that bound Zero,
then them killing
those council members...
Yes. If Tartaros kills all
the councilmen who sealed Face,
then the spell will be broken.
We've seen no signs
of interrogation,
which makes me think they might
already know where Face is.
So all they gotta do is knock
off a few more council members,
and then they can eliminate
all magic? Screw that!
[MAKAROV] We need to
get those three protected
as fast as we can. You said
that the former chairman
can tell us who
they are, yes?
Yes. I'm all but certain.
[MAKAROV]
Drop everything else!
Find out where that
chairman lives!
We can assume that Tartaros
is looking for him as well.
Beat them!
We're on it, sir! We've
located the addresses
of sixteen other former
council members.
We've got people from our guild,
and a couple of others,
on the way to protect them.
Turns out that one
of those addresses
was the former
chairman's!
Send someone to him,
as quickly as possible!
[LAKI] One step ahead of you,
sir. They're already en route!
[LAKI] The two best
wizards we could send.
[LUCY] Erza and Mirajane
rush to the aid of Crawford,
former Chairman of
the Magic Council.
Unfortunately, Tartaros
has other plans for them.
Meanwhile, Doranbolt makes
a desperate decision.
One which he may come to regret.
In order to gain
information about Tartaros,
he strikes a deal with
none other than Cobra,
of the Oración Seis.
Next time: Tartaros Chapter -
Immorality and Sinners
The prayers of sinners.
Echoing across the wastes.