[NARRATOR] It's the final day
of the Grand Magic Games
and the fighting is intense, as
the most powerful wizards clash.
Natsu and his team have rescued
Lucy from the palace dungeon
with the help of a version
of her from the future.
But she brought grim news of
horrific events
that were to come.
Meanwhile, Princess Hisui
considered activating
the Eclipse Two project,
in the hopes it could stop
a swarm of ten thousand
dragons that were
predicted to lay waste
to the kingdom.
The future of humanity
itself is in grave danger,
and our heroes race
against time to save it!
Iron and shadow? How?
[GAJEEL] Heh-heh.
I had no idea.
Has he always been able
to use two
attributes like this?
This definitely wasn't
a part of my strategy.
But it will help us.
If I hadn't seen it
with my own eyes,
I'd never have believed it.
Oh man! That guy is like
a freakin' monster now!
Well, he's always
had it in him, hasn't he?
[HAPPY] Roaring Thunder!
[cheering]
[CHAPATI] Holy cow! I have
never seen anything like this
in my life!
Mister Yajima,
where do you think the match
will go from here?
[YAJIMA] I'm afraid
I couldn't tell you.
Dragon Slayers do
generally defy all logic
and common sense,
in my opinion.
[MATO] That's true,
and don't forget that Rogue
is a third generation
dragon slayer!
I think the little punkin
is just getting started!
[scoffs]
It's impressive.
[SHADOW ROGUE] But still,
I have to strike you down.
[grunts]
He's gone!
No. He became a shadow.
[SHADOW ROGUE] How dare you
use my magic against me?
[SHADOW ROGUE] Predictable.
[SHADOW ROGUE grunts]
[GAJEEL chuckles]
[CHAPATI]
Whoa! That's incredible!
So now we gotta
watch two shadows fight?
That's a bit confusing.
It's practically impossible
to tell them apart.
[MATO] Oh wow!
I have no clue of
what's going on right now.
How am I gonna be able
to do a play-by-play
on something I can't
even see? Sorry folks.
[CHAPATI] All I can say is
something crazy is going on!
Bixlow.
Can you see anything?
Well, it's kinda tough
to make out their souls
through the monitor. But...
[BIXLOW] Gajeel's the
faster one, I think. Probably.
[EVERGREEN] Probably?
[SHADOW ROGUE] Uh! No!
[SHADOW ROGUE] He's pulling
me out of my shadow!
[groans]
[chuckles]
[SHADOW ROGUE] I never
dreamed he was this powerful!
[GAJEEL] Say goodnight!
[groans]
[GAJEEL]
Iron Shadow Dragon Roar!
[SHADOW ROGUE yells]
[ALL gasp]
[CANA giggles softly]
[ALL chuckle softly]
[distant crash]
[GAJEEL panting]
[CHAPATI] Uh. Well.
I-I guess that's it.
The fight is over!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] The winner is Gajeel!
[MATO] I can't believe
what just happened!
That was absolutely riveting.
So, that victory gives
Fairy Tail one more point,
[CHAPATI]
for a total of fifty-one!
[MATO] Sabertooth is still in
the lead with fifty-five points,
but just few more losses
and it could be over!
[SHADOW ROGUE laughs]
I suppose I expected too
much from Rogue as he is now.
[GAJEEL] Eh. Huh?
[SHADOW ROGUE laughs]
Okay.
[FROSCH] Please, stop!
It's you.
He's hurt really bad.
Please don't kill him.
[GAJEEL grunts]
[GAJEEL] Don't worry.
The fight's over,
and that ain't my style.
[FROSCH gasps]
[ROGUE] Frosch.
[FROSCH] Rogue! You're okay!
Of course I am.
[FROSCH] I was so scared.
Hey, pal.
Wait. Why am I in pain?
[ROGUE] I lost, didn't I?
[GAJEEL] He doesn't
remember the fight.
That shadow.
Somethin' weird's going on.
[CHAPATI] Another intense
Dragon Slayer battle
in this year's
Grand Magic Games!
[MATO] That was so
strange and unexpected!
I think the fans will be talking
about that one for a long time!
It was a battle for the
history books that's for sure.
Yes! We're definitely
on a roll now,
wouldn't you say First Master?
We are.
[MAVIS] It's troubling.
That evil shadow.
A magic I've
never witnessed before.
[MALE SOLDIERS yell]
Fire Dragon Wing Attack!
Regulus Impact!
[MALE SOLDIERS scream]
Sky Dragon Roar!
[MALE SOLDIER 188A]
We need reinforcements here!
[MALE SOLDIER 188B]
They're coming from Sectors
seven and eight!
[MALE SOLDIER 188A] Outnumbering
them's our only chance!
[MALE SOLDIER 188C]
Let's get 'em!
[MALE SOLDIERS] Yeah!
[MALE SOLDIER 188D]
For the princess!
[MALE SOLDIER 188E]
Let's teach 'em a lesson!
[MALE SOLDIERS yell]
There are so many of them!
[FUTURE LUCY] We shouldn't
have come this way!
We're going to make it, right?
We do have magic on our side.
It's super dangerous, Carla!
You should get back!
So should you!
Uh?
[PANTHERLILY] Get down!
[CARLA yells]
[chuckles]
Going somewhere, huh?
[HAPPY] Oh no!
[CARLA] An executioner!
Not you again!
[NEPPA laughs]
I still got a job
to do, pussycat!
[WENDY whimpers]
Hey cutie!
It's good to see you again.
But this will be the last time!
[FUTURE LUCY] No!
[LUCY] Horrible timing!
[KAMIKA] You were fools
to think you'd bested
the kingdom's mightiest
executioners.
Very foolish!
[KAMIKA] And the demon's
no longer with them.
Haul me in!
[MALE SOLDIERS]
Heave! Heave! Heave! Heave!
[KAMA] Guild wizards.
Huh?
[KAMA] I understand
what compels you.
But I must carry out my
obligation to the court.
For your crimes
against the kingdom,
I will be collecting your head.
Gimme a break. Again?
[MALE SOLDIER 188F]
Uh! We need to hurry!
[MALE SOLDIER 188G]
The Hungry Wolf Knights
have joined the battle!
[MALE SOLDIER 188H]
That's great news!
[MALE SOLDIER 188I]
Keep moving!
[MALE SOLDIER 188F,
188G, and 188H] Right!
[footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
[MALE SOLDIER 188J]
Uh. Colonel Arcadios!
[MALE SOLDIER 188K]
What are you doing here?
[MALE SOLDIER 188L]
I thought you were thrown in
the dungeon for treason!
Did you escape?
[ARCADIOS]
Where is the princess?
[MALE SOLDIER gasp]
I'm ordering you to tell me.
Sir. She's on the top floor.
[MALE SOLDIER 188M]
Do you see what he's wearing?
[MALE SOLDIER 188N] Yeah.
[MALE SOLDIER 188L]
It's the White Lily Armor!
[MALE SOLDIER 188K]
It's meant for combat!
[HISUI] I know it sounds
insane but hear me out.
They said there's
another way to use the gate.
They called it Eclipse Two.
[ARCADIOS] There is?
What does it entail?
I don't know if
you are aware of this,
but for the last seven
years we've used the games
to store magic power
within this gate.
[HISUI] The magic we've
accumulated within that time
is now as powerful
as an Etherion blast.
What?
It's on par with the sacred
light of the Magic Council?
[ARCADIOS] But it's said
that a single Etherion blast
can destroy
an entire nation!
[HISUI] This wealth
of magic power is the core
of the Eclipse Two.
And we shall unleash it
onto the swarm of dragons.
[FUTURE LUCY] If you
make it out of the castle
you'll need to
rendezvous with Jellal.
But be careful because
there are lacrimas
all over the city
monitoring the games.
That means you'll have to
take an underground route
to meet with him.
[NATSU] Wait. Him?
[FUTURE LUCY] I've
explained everything to him
as best I can.
I'm sure that he's busy coming
up with a plan as we speak.
Why's he coming up
with the plan?
[FUTURE LUCY] It's my fault.
I'm really sorry.
I probably should've come here
with some sort of strategy.
But to be honest, I don't know
what we can do to prevent it.
That's why I needed his help.
[ARCADIOS] I need to clear up
something that's troubling me.
[ARCADIOS] What I saw...
were surely not
the tears of a liar.
If anyone is not telling
the truth, it's the princess.
[CHAPATI] We are down
to the final three teams
in this year's
Grand Magic Games!
[MATO] Sabertooth is
holding on to their lead
with fifty-five points.
Fairy Tail is on their heels
with fifty-one points.
And Lamia Scale slithers into
third with forty-nine points!
Gajeel just scored
Fairy Tail's first point
in this round with
his win against Rogue.
[MATO] Yes that's true,
but Sabertooth still has
Sting and Minerva in play!
And they are a
couple of tough cookies!
[CHAPATI] Speaking of,
where is Sting, anyway?
[YAJIMA] Wherever he is,
I'm sure he has
some kind of plan in mind.
[ERZA] Damn you.
[MINERVA] You will be
next to fall, Erza.
And with that injury of yours,
it may prove
to be somewhat easy.
[ERZA gasps, screams]
[MINERVA chuckles]
[yells]
Erza!
How is this
even happening?
That injury must be
worse than we thought.
[ERZA grunts]
[CHAPATI] That's gotta hurt!
Titania is dropped to the
ground like a ton of bricks!
Minerva is just plain brutal!
[MINERVA] Pluck the
wings from a Fairy
and you will witness
a pathetic creature.
I suppose I should just
put you out of your misery.
Your life will be
ending here, Titania.
[growls]
No! You gotta get up, Erza!
[CHAPATI] This is the
most intense final round
I have ever seen
and it's not letting up!
Looks like we've got
an Ice Magic battle
being waged over here!
You're not as skilled as I am,
but you are persistent!
Ya still don't think
I've got any skills, huh?
Check this out!
[LYON grunts]
Juvia!
Ready! Water Nebula!
[GRAY] Ice Make: Shotgun!
Sky God Dance!
Good job, Shelia!
Why the heck are you
just standing there?
Now Gray, you'd really
stoop so low as to use
my love's magic against me?
You'll pay for that!
[SHELIA] Are you insane?
[LYON] Juvia would
never align herself
with a scumbag like you.
Huh?
Get your head in the game!
[LYON]
Ice Make. Water Serpent!
[GRAY groans]
Oh no, Gray!
Hey! Don't forget that
we're fighting her too!
[LYON]
I'm leaving that to you.
Careful. You're not
allowed to hurt her.
[SHELIA] What?
Lyon's powerful.
I really had no idea.
Yeah, but he totally
sucks at teamwork.
[GRAY] Let's use that
to our advantage!
[CHAPATI] This match has turned
in to a two-on-two battle.
What are your
thoughts, Mr. Yajima?
[YAJIMA] Gray and Lyon are
both quite handsome fellows,
I suppose.
[MATO] Uh... What does that
have to do with anything?
Well no matter what happens,
little Shelly-Welly
is gonna win this round!
[YAJIMA] Yeah, yeah.
[CROWD laughing]
[MALE SOLDIERS commotion]
Terrain Effect.
Scorching Wind Zone!
Oh yeah, you know
I love to feel the heat!
I'm all fired up!
Yeah?
[NATSU yells]
[UOSUKE] Uh-oh!
Terrain Effect: Iceberg Zone!
[NATSU] Aw man,
what a pain in the butt!
--[WENDY grunts]
--[NEPPA] Woo hoo!
Watch out! That acid's
gonna eat you alive!
[NEPPA laughs]
I hear that you're a
Dragon Slayer too, little girl!
[WENDY]
Yes I am! Why do you care?
[NEPPA] Pop!
Sky Dragon Wing Attack!
[NEPPA laughs] You're making
this extra fun for me!
Paper Blizzard. Red Dance!
Okay. Open Gate of
the Scorpion! Scorpio!
I got this! Wicked!
[KAMIKA] The yellow papers
hold the spirit of lightning.
[SCORPIO] Sand Wall!
I can't believe
I'm fighting a spirit!
This is a dream come true!
Your name's Cosmos, right?
You know, I'm really more
of a lover than a fighter.
We should
get to know each other.
--[PLANT MONSTER growls]
--[LOKE] Aah!
First off, I find men like
you completely revolting.
Your very existence
only cheapens true beauty.
[COSMOS] You should just die!
[LOKE]
I see. So you like to play
a little hard to get, do ya?
I understand,
and this is so sudden.
[COSMOS] You don't get it!
[LOKE] Maybe I should
sweeten the deal.
I have a couple of
presents for you.
And I've got the
perfect thing for you!
Spore Bomb! Rinka Renka!
[MALE SOLDIER 188A] Whoa!
[MALE SOLDIER 188B]
The Wolf Knights are awesome!
[MALE SOLDIER 188C] Let's get
in there and fight with them!
[PANTHERLILY] Not happening!
[MALE SOLDIERS yell]
[BOTH grunting]
I've heard about you.
The rumors say that you used to
be a soldier but you deserted.
[KAMA] Why did you
shirk your sacred duty?
[PANTHERLILY grunts]
Someone like you would never
understand what happened!
[KAMA] Let me guess.
You felt that your kingdom
had lost its moral compass.
Bite your tongue, executioner.
I will not tolerate you
insulting Edolas!
[KAMA] Come!
[PANTHERLILY grunts]
[NATSU grunts]
What's wrong?!
This too much for ya?
You look plum tuckered out!
Ya know, it doesn't
really matter how I'm feelin'.
And it doesn't matter how many
of you jokers there are, either.
[NATSU] We are gonna
get out of here! End of story!
You can keep gettin' in
our way and slowing us down.
But you are never
gonna stop Fairy Tail!
[CHAPATI] Hold on!
We've got another wizard
joining the party, folks!
[MATO] It's the Wizard Saint,
Jura Nekis!
This is gonna be a doozy!
[JURA] I hope you don't mind
me interrupting your fight.
It's simply
too enticing to pass up.
[LAXUS] So the
monster shows himself.
[laughs]
Oh, this is gonna be good.
Laymia Scale won this
whole stinkin' tournament
the moment Jura
was chosen to participate.
Those two little babies
he just walked up to
don't stand
a chance against him.
I wouldn't wanna be them.
That's for sure.
But it ain't fair!
Way to keep your cool.
You lost big time.
I'll spin you!
You are spinnin' me!
[LAXUS]
He's not foolin' around.
Don't be afraid, Laxus!
I have complete
and total faith in you!
The Thunder Legion's
got your back, man!
I've never seen him
this nervous before.
[grunts]
[OLGA] All right,
come on and join the party.
I'd love to
see you fight for real.
Let's see if you've got the
stones to try and stop this.
[JURA] Oh?
I'm gonna give you a taste
of my full power, old man.
[OLGA] Let's answer the question
that's on everyone's mind.
Who's magic is stronger,
a saint, or a god slayer?
Are you up for the challenge?
You can walk away.
Is that Wizard Saint
title just for show?
[JURA] I'll play.
[chuckles]
[LAXUS] He walked
right into his trap.
He's actually falling for that?
Don't do it!
Shut up! Or I'll spin you!
[SHERRY and TOBY]
You are spinning me!
Here goes! Lightning God.
Charged Particle Cannon!
[gasps]
[ALL yell]
[ALL gasp]
[JURA] I remember you now.
You fought on the
very first day of the games.
[groans]
[ALL gasp]
[JURA] That fight ended
with one blow as well.
[CROWD murmurs]
[CROWD cheering]
[CHAPATI] And with
that devastating face palm,
Lamia Scale trails
Fairy Tail by one point!
[MAKAROV] Aah!
He doesn't have a chance.
Master, how can you
say such a thing?
Have just a
little faith in Laxus!
Yeah, he can totally
take down that old guy!
[JURA] Now that's done.
[scoffs]
[OHBA chuckles]
You should just pack
it in, Makarov.
A lot happened in the seven
years that you were gone.
Namely, Jura rose
to be number five among
the ten Wizard Saints.
Yeah, and those four
that are above him
are totally
impossible to beat.
[OHBA] How dare you
mention them! I'll spin you!
[SHERRY] You are spinning me!
[OHBA] The Ishgar Four.
They're not even human.
Which means Jura is the
most powerful human wizard.
He won't lose.
[MAVIS] Jura Nekis. The one
who gave me the most anxiety
in this final battle.
There's nothing
I can do now, boy.
Just watch,
and pray for the best.
I had been hoping I would
get the opportunity
to spar with you.
The grandson of Makarov.
[LAXUS] All right,
you can stop right there.
I don't need the baggage.
You can just forget
about your fancy title
and who I'm related to.
You and I are just two men.
So be it.
[LAXUS and JURA grunt]
[grunts]
[LAXUS bellows]
[LAXUS groans]
[ALL gasp]
[CHAPATI] Whoa!
Lightning has been struck!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[CHAPATI]
Man. Down in a single blow.
I'm at a loss for words.
[MATO] He squashed him.
[CHAPATI] Well, uh,
that's one way to put it.
In this world, there's
always someone above you.
[LAXUS] Yeah,
you're right about that.
But what you
seem to have forgotten...
is to pay close attention
to who's right at your feet!
[grunts]
[HAPPY] Wow, we're finally
coming to the end
of the Grand Magic Games!
[NATSU] Oh yeah! We made it to
the finish line, little buddy!
[HAPPY] This has been
a crazy ride, huh?
[NATSU]
Ha! You can say that again!
[HAPPY] There are still
some super tough folks left
to take down,
but we can do it, right?
[NATSU] You know it! Fairy Tail
is gonna take the top spot!
[NATSU and HAPPY]
Next time: Gloria!
[HAPPY] I can practically
taste victory! Come on, guys!
[NATSU] Just one last push!
We're counting on ya!