[SILVER]
This body is just a vessel.
I happened upon
some random corpse.
[GRAY]
Uh.
[SILVER] You know that
every member of Tartaros
is a demon from Zeref's books,
don't you? Myself included.
In fact, my true form
isn't even remotely human.
But still, you can probably
imagine how hard it is
to blend in when you go around
looking like a big, scary demon.
That's why I needed a human
"costume," if you will.
When the time finally
rolled around
to pick which one I wanted, of
course, I had to choose the one
that still had all
his body parts intact.
Honestly, I've kind of grown
attached to this old thing.
Anyway, I didn't have
any ulterior motives
for throwing this one on,
just convenience.
But somehow it's what brought
you and I together again.
This day has been a
long time coming, my boy.
I've been hungry for
the taste of your blood.
You're about one second
away from a beat down!
I still don't have a clue
what in the hell
you're talking about!
Why are you really using
my dad's body like this?
And why do you want
to use it to kill me?
You wanna know?!
Because I won't be satisfied
until I've killed everyone
that witch Ur cared about!
[growls]
[SILVER]
After all,
she put me in that prison
of ice for ten years.
[GRAY]
What?
[SILVER]
I'm not Silver, I'm Deliora!
There's no way in hell
you've forgotten my name!
No way.
Ur killed Deliora. I saw it!
[SILVER]
Yes, that is true.
I was dead for ten long years.
But once Tartaros built the
Hell's Core regeneration system,
it gave me another chance
to get my sweet revenge.
You're here for revenge? Really?
I know how that feels.
If you're having a
hard time believing me,
I can show you my true form.
You know, the one
from your nightmares.
The monster that killed
your whole family!
[growling]
[GRAY panting]
Heh.
Deliora!
Ur's little shadow
is here to play.
[SILVER laughing]
[GRAY grunts]
Damn!
Oh, please!
You'll need to defend yourself
a lot better than that, kiddo!
[GRAY groans]
Pull yourself together!
I'm tryin' to wring some
satisfaction outta this!
[GRAY growls]
Come on, boy!
I killed your dad. Take revenge!
Is this all you learned from Ur?
[GRAY]
Ice Make Cold Excalibur!
[laughing]
[SILVER]
I gotta admit.
Ice magic ain't bad at all.
It's a powerful weapon
in the right hands.
Just not in yours.
[SILVER] I've tasted bland
ice before, but wow.
[GRAY grunts]
No snappy retort?
Somethin' ya might'a picked up
from your flamethrower friend:
you don't attack a slayer
with his own kinda magic.
[SILVER laughs]
[GRAY growls]
[SILVER] Ice is the only
weapon Ur's clan has.
Which is precisely why
I mastered a magic
impervious to it.
Ice Demon Slayer magic!
[JUVIA]
Demon Slayer Magic?
[KEYES] Yes. An ironic
skill to possess in an ally.
He became one of
the Demon Gates
at the behest of
the Underworld King
in recognition of his might.
If he's really a demon slayer,
then why is he
on Tartaros' side?
[KEYES] Perhaps our
powers changed his mind.
Or perhaps he plots
against us from within.
Regardless, I'm certain
my dread sovereign
had his reasons for
recruiting such a man.
[JUVIA]
Hang in there, Gray.
[NATSU yells]
Ker-plunk
[NATSU groans]
That didn't even leave a
scratch, you mumbling freak!
I'm just fine.
[TEMPESTER]
"Mumbling freak"?
Shall I take that as an
attempt to mock me, human?
[LUCY]
Those curses. Calamities.
Like the plague that got to
Laxus and the Thunder Legion!
Could this be the guy?!
Yeah, I get it; you're strong.
Now lemme tan your scaly hide!
Ha. I've never seen
a human like you.
But regardless!
You're under a
certain delusion.
Seems you think you're the
toughest thing you've ever seen.
Back where we demons are from,
such bluster marks a fool.
You sound angry.
I didn't say anything to
hurt your feelings, did I?
Well, if I can piss you off,
I know I can make you cry.
So how's this sound?
I'ma beat on ya till
you cry out for mercy!
Swoosh and slash.
[NATSU screams]
[GAJEEL grunts]
Come on, guys. Hang in there!
[NATSU grunts]
[GAJEEL]
What's the matter, Salamander?
Your butt looks a little raw!
[NATSU] Naw, Happy's snowballs
hit harder than this guy.
Glad to hear it.
Mine's no pushover,
but I like him for that.
Let's end this freak show!
They screwed with
the wrong guild!
[NATSU screams]
I'm sorry, everyone.
I just need a little more
time to get it together.
[exposion]
[LUCY]
Juvia!
[KEYES] I have a question
for you, water wielder.
What is it that you fear most?
Losing the one you love, surely.
But what would be worse?
To slowly earn his hatred,
or find yourself abandoned
to his indifference?
Perhaps the least painful way to
lose him would be through death.
[JUVIA] Silence, fiend! I'm
immune to your verbal abuse!
[KEYES]
Is that a fact?
Gray and I have been together
for hundreds of days, okay?
We are way past
the hatred phase,
and he's in too deep
to abandon me now.
So yes, you might as
well save your breath.
[KEYES]
You're unaffected.
My, what a pleasant surprise.
[TEMPESTER]
Guzzle.
[NATSU grunts]
Ka-bam.
[NATSU groans]
[TEMPESTER]
Thud.
[NATSU groans]
[LUCY]
Natsu!
[NATSU yells]
[GRAY groaning]
[SILVER]
Yeah, that's it.
That's the look I've
been waitin' to see.
I'm gonna twist that pretty
face of yours with pain.
Oh, and after I'm
finished with you,
I'm gonna hunt
down your pal Lyon.
And once I've bled him dry,
I'll move on to
everyone else you know.
Every friend you've
ever had is gonna die.
[GRAY growls]
That isn't your mouth
to use, so shut it!
You're never gonna
hurt anyone again!
You hear me?!
Ice Impact!
Now that ice tasted good.
[growls]
[SILVER]
Here comes mine.
Ice Demon
Rage!
[GRAY grunting]
[SILVER laughing]
[SILVER]
Do you like it?
[laughing]
I know you're gonna be
a strong man, Gray.
Word of advice for ya.
Get out of my father
and then run
before I realize how
pissed off I am.
[SILVER]
Ooh, you've got me shaking
in my ice resistant
boots, tough guy.
There's nothin' you can
do to hurt me, remember?
Ice only makes me stronger!
[GRAY]
Ice Make...
Cannons!
This is pathet--
[groans]
[SILVER]
Ah, I get it.
Those cannons might
be made of ice,
but you've got 'em loaded
with regular rocks.
Good!
You're smarter than
I took ya for!
However...
[GRAY]
What the--?
[SILVER] There a problem?
Thought you liked it cold.
You're gonna have
a hell of a time
finding more
ice-free ammo now.
No, there's ammo everywhere.
[SILVER]
Huh?
[GRAY] Found out somethin'
about this kinda ice
back at the Village of the Sun.
I can channel it through my body
to reshape it any way I please!
[gasps] What do you mean?!
As you've repeatedly mentioned,
Slayer Wizards can consume
any magic of their elements.
But I'm pretty sure there's
an exception to that.
No way, man. I can't
just eat my own fire.
What, are you crazy?
[GRAY growls, yells]
This one's for my
entire frickin' family!
[SILVER] You're right,
I can't consume my own magic.
But it's still ice.
And ice can't hurt me.
How long's it gonna take
before you realize
what you're up against?
It's me, Gray. Deliora
come to take your life!
[GRAY whimpers]
[groaning]
[FRANMALTH] Ah! Oh, what
a humiliating blunder.
I'll never live it down!
[groans] Captured
by a pack of cats!
How much will
this failure cost?!
That's one noisy shroom.
It was less annoying
on top of my head.
I wonder why it
became a mushroom.
I'm feelin' hungry again.
Anyone mind if I eat it?
Sorry, but somethin' tells
me that's not a good idea.
So what's the deal with
this mushroom anyway?
Had ya seen it before,
or did it pop up at random?
I've seen it before, all right.
It's one of Tartaros' strongest!
Natsu beat him up earlier,
but it was a crazy hard fight.
He swallows people's souls
and takes their power!
Celestial Spirits, too!
Also, I guess spells have souls
cause they're on the menu.
[PANTHERLILY]
You're rambling, Happy.
But the point of it is, he
has powerful curses, right?
So is this guy
turning into a fungus
like a symbol of his
parasitic nature?
Yeah, I couldn't tell ya.
[ALL gasp]
He's yucky.
[CATS]
Ah!
[FRANMALTH] Evil, wicked cats
trying to eat me alive.
[LECTOR]
We've talked about this, Frosch.
If your food can move,
ya gotta cook it.
Not fish, but the point
is we gotta wait
till he shows us the control
room, or else Erza'll kill us.
Sorry about that.
[PANTHERLILY]
You guys are, kind of cruel.
[FRANMALTH] "Cruel"?!
They're positively demonic!
You shut your
filthy demon mouth.
Now listen,
you'll take us to the control
room and you'll do it quickly.
And should I sense that
you've lead us astray,
so help me, I will slice
you up and sauté you myself!
[LECTOR]
Hey! Erza and Minerva are back.
[FROSCH] Oh good!
I hope they brought food.
There's no time!
We gotta stop all those
Faces from blowin'up first.
Right, and we don't even
have an hour to do it.
We musn't dawdle.
[FRANMALTH] I can't
afford to take them there,
but I can't afford to get
chopped up and eaten, either.
I have to buy some time somehow!
[CARLA]
There are so many of them.
What can we do
against such odds?
Hey, Doranbolt,
how long would it take us
to get back to Magnolia
if you used a direct line?
I might have to stop a
few times along the way
to get my bearings.
But I'd say about five
minutes, give or take.
So are we regrouping
with the others?
Yes, but that's not the
only thing we're doing.
We'll use Warren's
magic to tell the other guilds
about these Faces,
and ask for their help.
If we're gonna succeed, we'll
need every last one of them.
And this is one fight that
all of us have a stake in.
[DORANBOLT]
Let's move.
[WENDY, CARLA]
Right!
[KEYES laughs]
What's the matter?
Is your resolve
beginning to waver?
[JUVIA gasps]
[KEYES]
I see it clearly.
Soon enough, your beloved
will choose to make the same
sacrifice his master did.
[JUVIA]
What is he saying?
That Gray will
use... Iced Shell?
What's the deal? You
were talkin' so big before.
You're not wimpin' out, are ya?
--[SILVER chuckles]
--[GRAY groans]
Well, if you're all outta talk,
then the least you
can do is scream!
There's no need to be
shy about it. Let it out.
What's the point in killing you,
if you haven't given up?!
[GRAY groaning]
[SILVER]
Louder!
I want you to know
you've lost before you die.
Know that all your righteous
anger counts for nothing!
That pain and fear
is all you have!
[SILVER]
That putrid taste in your mouth?
They call it despair.
I'm the wolf, and
you're the lamb,
so you never had chance, boy!
[GRAY grunts]
[GRAY]
Chance, or no, I will win.
Cause I have to!
[SILVER]
Uh... Hmph.
You're never even gonna
get near my friends!
[SILVER] The human
heart's a stupid thing;
it hopes without reason.
Ice can't hurt me.
And everything
here's covered in it.
That means you lose.
Not yet. There's still one
spell I can stop you with.
[SILVER gasps]
You might remember this one.
[SILVER]
You're obviously bluffing.
I've already proven that
ice attacks can't hurt me.
Are you gonna throw away
your life to prove me right?
You really won't stand a
chance once you're dead.
[SILVER] Why would
you go through with this?
We both know it won't work!
[GRAY]
What makes you so sure?
Think back. This spell made
a statue of you, didn't it?
That was then!
Before I learned to wield
Ice Demon Slayer magic;
it's different now!
You may be right!
But if you know for sure, then
why do you look so scared?!
You aren't really gonna do this.
You wouldn't dare! You'll die!
There's no question! I'll
do anything to stop you!
No! Don't do it!
You killed my family.
[SILVER gasps]
An illusion.
[GRAY]
And then.
[SILVER whimpers]
You killed my master, too!
No, wait!
[NATSU]
If I didn't let you do it before
why would I let you do it now?
I'm not gonna let you
go out like that.
I love you, Gray!
[GRAY]
I'm sorry!
Iced Shell!
[SILVER screams]
Now freeze!
Ice has no effect on me!
I will never freeze again!
[GRAY gasps]
You just gave your
life for nothing!
The Iced Shell has failed!
[GRAY] I'm sorry...
I came close...
To forgettin' about
the people in my life!
[SILVER] What? They
were both illusions?
[GRAY]
I refuse to die!
My friend would get
way too sappy if I did!
A cannon ball? How the
hell did you get it?!
[GRAY]
Melted the ice around it.
Just like in the
Village of the Sun.
[SILVER]
Uh.
[SILVER] It wasn't the
dragon slayer. It was you.
[GRAY]
Ice Make...
Vambrace!
[SILVER groaning]
Knew ya had it in you.
[GRAY panting]
Damn it!
Did you think I
wouldn't realize?!
Just how stupid
do you think I am?
[GRAY]
Damn it, why?!
Why?!
[GRAY pants] You lied to
me. You aren't Deliora.
You're my dad.
I know you are.
[LUCY] Once torn apart by a
demon's murderous rampage,
father and son
share a sad reunion.
Resurrected by
Tartaros's necromancer
and forced to serve amongst
their ranks for far too long,
Silver never lost sight
of his one true goal.
Now he tells his final tale,
and gives Gray his inheritance.
Next time: "Tartaros Chapter
A Silver Wish."
His face is cleaved with tears,
the raking claws of truth.