[ALL]
Cheers!
Man, I can't believe we
get to go to the beach
with a veritable harem of
bathing beauties on our arms!
Can't wait to squirt my
sunscreen all over their backs.
[JUNICHI] Yeah. It's gonna
be epic, for sure.
We'll have to plan it carefully,
down to the last detail.
The grade school girls will be
out on summer vacation, too.
I'll teach them how
to hold their breath?
But all that fun's
gonna cost money.
We may have to get part-time
jobs to save up for this.
Must be some other way.
Can't we just sell our blood
or sperm or something?
I should learn mouth-to-mouth
in case I get lucky
and one of 'em drowns.
Don't worry about it.
I have the perfect
jobs lined up for us.
A job at a manga shop?
Considering how much of a
fanboy you've been lately,
I figured you could handle it.
Put some of your ding dong
geek knowledge to good use.
[KEIGO] I love you,
stain-resistant love pillow!
All right! I can do it!
Oh, and I'll be there,
too, co-worker.
Minoru, somehow you passed
the background check for this.
[chuckling]
[MINORU]
I didn't even think of this!
[SHINPEI] I'm just trying
to speed up your journey
to rock bottom.
[JUNICHI]
Hey, what about me?
Picked this one just for you.
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
I have to wear that?!
[SHINPEI] That's right,
you'll be a pretty little maid.
Kissass.
Look closer. You'll be
working in the kitchen.
Like anybody wants to see you in
fishnets and cat ears, Kissass.
Quit calling me that.
[MINORU] If one of the girls has
a small crush, what can I do?
[SHINPEI]
Shut the hell up!
So anyway, if we wanna show
the ladies a good time,
we're gonna have to pull
in some serious cash flow.
Whaddaya say, gentlemen?
[ALL]
Yeah!
And if I'm really lucky,
one of 'em might even
have a younger sister
who's in kindergarten, too.
Hey. Shinpei.
Was Toranoana
always this scary?
Uh-uh.
Nah, usually the worst
thing about this place
is all the nerd B.O.
[TORANOANA MANAGER A
clears throat]
'Kay, I want all of
these on the shelf
within the next ten minutes.
Man, who'd'a thought a
job catering to nerds
would require so much
friggin' athletic ability?
Not to mention
it's hot as balls.
Well, crap, I think I threw
out my wanking shoulder.
[MINORU] Every day, you're
getting a little bit older.
It's life's greatest tragedy.
[SHINPEI]
Keigo. Call the police.
...way to show you how I truly
feel would, technically,
be a felony.
[SHINPEI]
I need to bleach my eyeballs.
[giggles]
All right. Let's do this.
[ALL] It's so good to see
you, oh great master.
[JUNICHI gasping]
What are you guys
all doing here?
What's it look like,
silly? We're working.
[NENE]
Junichi!
Did you come just to
see me dressed all sexy?
What? Why?
Aren't you happy that Mister
Virgin popped in to see you?
Um, of course I'm not happy!
Oh, but wait, Junichi,
you can't be here.
We aren't open yet.
No, see, I'm gonna
be working here, too.
You know this is a
cosplay café, right?
[NENE]
Well, I can't wait to see
what you look like
dressed in cosplay.
[giggles]
[JUNICHI]
No, I'm--
What're you cosplaying? The
virgin lead of a harem anime?
Of all places, why do you
have to work here, huh?
[JUNICHI]
Uh.
Oh, well, Shinpei
set this up for me.
Also, for the record,
I'm not doing any cosplay.
I'm on kitchen duty.
[door opens]
[CAFÉ MANAGER A]
Mh-hm-hm.
[CAFÉ MANAGER A chuckles]
[CAFÉ MANAGER A smells]
Ah, your outfits are nice.
Now give our fans plenty
of service. Wink-wink.
You startin' today, cheese dick?
Oh, me? Uh, yeah.
Thanks for the
opportunity, sir.
[CAFÉ MANAGER A Whatever,
you white-palmed squeeze boy.
[YUKANA giggles]
[YUKANA]
Here you go, big boy.
Um, would you mind casting
a spell over my food
to make it taste better?
Yeah, okay.
Here goes, all right.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boobs in
pasties, be more tasty!
Whoa! I think I just
bukakied my khakis!
[NENE] A love-shot shot
straight through your heart!
Bang-bang, cowboy!
[MAN B]
Oh, mama! That was awesome!
Straight to my heart
and right to my groin!
[MAN C]
'Scuse me, miss.
Sorry, I'll be right th-- Oh.
Ow.
Oh, zowie! Are you
a clumsy girl?
This is so unbelievably
embarrassing.
Thank y-- Uh. Aw...
[CUSTOMER A]
Whoops.
[RANKO chuckles]
Did you get too excited?
There we go.
Uh, so, I got some
on my clothes, too.
You think maybe you could
rub me off down there?
[RANKO]
Sorry, sir.
But these rags won't
work on that mess,
so I'll just have to
use this on it instead!
[yelps] Never mind!
[RANKO]
Miracles and magic do exist!
[thud]
[SHINPEI]
There. There. There.
All right, boss, I'm done
stockin' the shelves.
Okay, then why don't you start
putting out the light nov--?
Already done, sir.
I went ahead and set up
the staff recommendation
display, as well.
[TORANOANA MANAGER A]
Oh.
Then, uh, how about
checking the invoice--?
[SHINPEI]
Did it during my break.
And then I verbally
abused the supplier
about some items
that never arrived.
Think I made 'em pee a little.
[TORANOANA MANAGER A]
Ah. Well.
And also, I put together
a list of titles
that I believe would sell quite
well with our customers.
For your consideration,
of course.
[TORANOANA MANAGER A]
Hmm.
You brown-nosing bastard.
Good morning--
[YUI gasps]
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
[screams]
[JUNICHI sighs]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
[YUKANA]
You were peeping on Yui?
Huh? I didn't mean to.
It was an accident.
When I walked in,
she just happened to be
changing, that's all.
How dare you!
I don't believe it!
And of course,
I'm wearing something
super embarrassing, too.
That creepazoid manager sure
has some weird fetishes.
[YUKANA groans]
[YUKANA]
So hot.
[JUNICHI] They're s'posed
to be fixing it tomorrow.
[YUKANA]
What?
But it's hot today. This sucks.
Ooh, that looks good.
Uh. Wait, I already
drank outta that.
[YUKANA]
Here you go. Thanks.
Oh. Right.
[JUNICHI] Does an
indirect kiss with Yukana
still count as a real kiss?
So much boob sweat.
Break time, bitches!
[yells]
Oh, my bad.
[JUNICHI]
My almost-first kiss is trash!
Well, recycling,
but still. Trash!
[TORANOANA MANAGER A]
I'm leaving the store
in Shinpei's hands while
I step out for a bit.
Listen up!
As your leader, I will double,
no, triple, this store's sales!
We'll be the number one
store in the franchise,
in the entire industry,
the best ever!
So terrificly good, people.
You know it, I know it,
together, we can make
Toranoana great again!
[KEIGO]
This speech sounds familiar...
[SHINPEI]
Hmm...
[JUNICHI]
Phew.
Man, today was brutal.
Oh, but wait, tomorrow's
my last day, right?
[JUNICHI]
It's a theme day.
But which pervy fetish
is it this time?
[chuckling]
[CAFÉ MANAGER A] I've made
yet another brilliant choice.
Tomorrow should be
quite stimulating.
[chuckling]
Book Girl Day?
What's that mean?
Well, we wear these
cute outfits,
and then we read novels
to the customers.
Sounds super classy, yeah?
Oh, I wanted to ask which of
these books you like best.
[RANKO]
'Sup, bitches?
[YUKANA]
Hey!
Are you picking the books?
Yeah, you should.
You read these things.
[RANKO]
This sucks donkey balls.
Though, we do get a bonus,
so I guess it's not all bad.
"All of a sudden, the
prudish girl had morphed
from a virtuous young woman
into a perverted, dirty slut"?
Oh my God!
"Moans, kisses, and
grunts filled the room.
'It's so hard,' she exclaimed.
Himekawa's body secreted
its own lubrication of love."
Ugh!
"She screamed, 'I-I can feel
it deep inside of my-my--'"
What the hell is this?
I-I can't read this sick,
misogynistic crap!
What is that creep thinking?
It's downright degrading!
I'll be right back!
Wonder what she's up to.
She's one salty bitch.
The Covenant of
Sister New Goddess ?
"An erotic light novel"?
[NENE ] Nousui ?
Junior High School ExD ?
Hybrid x Heart Magias
Academy Ataraxia ?
I feel like you had
this one, didn't you?
Whoa, those are really bad!
Like, really, really bad!
"Sylvia's breasts had
never been touched before,
but like a brave explorer,
Kizuna's hand was first to
traverse the snowy mounds.
'Ah! Ah! Wait, Captain, I'm--'
'What's wrong, Sylvia,
are you not fondle this?'"
Does this stuff send
blood to your rod?
[JUNICHI]
Uh.
"'Oh, please, I want you
to put it inside of me.'
Kizuna aligned his core with
her patiently waiting entrance
and slowly pushed in."
[NENE moaning]
[JUNICHI] Uh! Nene, stop!
Whatever you do--
"'Oh, Sylvia, I can't
take it anymore!
Here I go, Sylvia, I'm gonna
explode all over your--"
[RANKO]
Yoink.
Aw, but it was just
about to get good.
[RANKO chuckles]
This is making Mister
Virgin act all squirmy,
so I want in on the fun, too.
You ready?
"The energy that was generated
by passion inside the Love Room
transferred to the pyramid.
'Please, make me your slave!
Make me my master's slave!'
'Good. You said it correctly
that time, Yurishia.'
And Kizuna rewarded his slave
by making the wooden
horse vibrate."
[JUNICHI] Ranko, just drop it!
This next part gets super dirty!
[chuckles]
"On her hands and
knees, she begged,
'Please, put it right here.'.
Then she used her delicate
fingers to open up
her most precious part,
just below her balloon knot."
[RANKO snickers]
[RANKO laughs]
Look, Mister Virgin's
face is turning beet red!
[JUNICHI] What? No!
Your face is red! Shut up!
[RANKO] "'Uh! Ooh, I've never
felt this good before!'
She lifted her ass high,
and began to convulse like an
epileptic catfish, crying,
'Oh! Spank me, please!'"
[YUKANA] 'Kay, it's
my turn to read some.
You really don't
have to, Yukana.
"In Kizuna's mind,
it felt to him like
he was thrusting
deep inside of Aine.
And at the same time,
like he was penetrating
Grace's sacred place, too.
It was a most
powerful sensation,
as though he were violating
the two sisters,
both Aine and Grace,
simultaneously.
An out-of-this-world feeling
of pleasure and euphoria
overcame his entire body.
Its intensity was so great,
Kizuna was convinced
his brain would soon
melt like chocolate."
[YUKANA]
"'It feels so good on--'"
[JUNICHI]
Stop it!
That's enough!
This has gone too far!
[CAFÉ MANAGER A] What are
you getting your panties
in a twist about now?
[JUNICHI]
Sir.
Well, ladies, are you ready?
Pick out your books yet?
I laid out only
the best for you,
so you really can't go wrong.
They're sure to
whet your interest.
You're crossing a line!
You can't make high school
girls read that crap!
Ah, come on they're just
some light novels.
[JUNICHI]
They may be light novels,
but they're heavy on
the creepy sex stuff!
[CAFÉ MANAGER A]
Of course!
Where's the fun in forcing
these jailbait tricks
to read something "decent"?
Plus, most of the freaks who
come in here hate women,
so seeing girls degraded
gives 'em boners
and makes 'em happy!
Well, maybe think about how
these girls feel for once!
Maybe they don't
wanna be debased
just so you can sell a few
more shitty chicken wings
to horny losers
with mommy issues!
[CAFÉ MANAGER A growls]
Check out the balls on this kid!
Come in here and lecture
me, you dickless cuck!
Uh, boss.
It's for you.
Me?
[YUI]
It's the owner of the café.
You're shittin' me, right?
Hey, Yui, so what's up?
No, sir. Sorry about that.
Yes, sir. Of course, I'll take
care of it right away, sir.
Yes, sir. Of course.
Once again, I'm so sorry.
Yes, sir. Please don't fire me.
[CAFÉ MANAGER A] Book Day's
been cancelled, you guys.
Another win for you
SJW Millenials.
Tch.
Oh, but, boss?
We're still getting that bonus
you promised, aren't we?
Fine. Whatever.
That was amazing!
So the call from the
owner, that was all you?
Hashtag boss bitch!
Ha. Not bad for
a stuck-up bitch.
Wait, I'm confused.
[YUKANA] I'm like literally so
happy Book Girl Day got the axe.
There's no way I
coulda read that stuff
in front of a buncha randos.
Yeah, that guy was a tool.
What's wrong?
Why're you staring at me?
Do I have something on my face?
Nah, I was just thinking.
You were kinda badass today.
Huh? In what way?
Oh, just 'cause.
Y'know, working part-time was
actually kinda fun, though.
Yeah 'cept for
that mega-creeper.
All right, so besides
cosplay waitress,
what else do you wanna be?
[YUKANA]
Hmm...
Lemme think a sec.
I guess I wouldn't
mind being a hostess
at a bomb-ass karaoke joint.
[JUNICHI chuckles]
Oh, yeah, now that sounds like
it'd be right up your alley.
You would make a killer
karaoke hostess.
Right? But I want you there
right by my side, boyfriend.
Wait, I have to
work there, too?
Duh. Well, it's not
just at work though.
I wanna do lots
of stuff with you.
Yeah, like what?
Let's see. Hmm...
Well, like hang out
together, eat together,
walk home together.
Uh, we do all of
that now, silly.
'Kay, what else?
I wanna spend Christmas
with you, birthdays, too,
and buy each other
matching stuff.
Huh? Like what kinda
matching stuff?
All kinds ya know.
Like cell phone straps.
And, y'know, like key chains.
We can post profile
pictures together.
Oh, uh. Heh. No,
it's nothing. Never mind.
[JUNICHI chuckles]
So the beach'll be fun.
With Shinpei and Ranko and
all the rest of 'em there,
there's sure to be all
kinds of hijinks, huh?
Hey, Junichi?
'Sup?
I know we're going to the
beach with the whole crew,
but we should try
to go somewhere
with just the two of us, too.
Whoa, just us two?
[YUKANA giggles]
Yeah, just us two!
[YUKANA]
'S everyone here?
[ALL]
Yeah!
Cool! Then let's go hit
the beach, you ready?
[OTHERS]
Yeah!
[JUNICHI]
Let's go!
[AYUMI]
Yo, Ayumi here!
[KOKORO]
And Kokoro!
[AYUMI] Oh, look,
the big shot protagonist
has come to steal
our screen time!
[KOKORO]
With his big swingin' dick!
[JUNICHI]
Sorry, I don't know what to say.
[AYUMI]
Then don't say anything!
You're eating up
our time, virgin!
[KOKORO]
Yeah, you virgin!
[JUNICHI]
Hey, you girls are mean!
[AYUMI]
Say, you're the protagonist.
Do you have any
pull around here?
[KOKORO] Yeah, can you
get us more screen time?
[JUNICHI]
I really don't like being here.
[AYUMI, KOKORO]
Then just leave already!
[JUNICHI]
This whole preview was just me
getting dragged by you two!