[BRO C]
Huh? Who's this scrote licker?
[DAI] Oh, it's Yukana's
lame-o boyfriend.
Ugh. What a drag.
So I guess you heard
all that, huh?
[JUNICHI]
Take it back.
[DAI]
Huh?
Take what back, dingleberry?
Yukana is not a slut!
Aw, sad. Does your twat hurt?
[DAI chuckles]
[BRO C]
Please let me just kick his ass.
Ah, come on,
who we kiddin' here?
Just look at her.
That slut's the sluttiest
slut that ever slutted.
Yukana isn't a slut,
you STD-ridden cheese dick!
Ugh. Yo, dude, take your
TED Talk somewhere else.
I'll be damned if
I'm gonna let Yukana
end up with a
douchebag like you!
[laughs]
Oh, no, you're a
virgin, aren't you?
Might as well have it
tattooed on your face,
the way you're actin'.
That's why that
fine-as-hell slut
is totally playin' your ass!
[JUNICHI growls]
Take it back!
Take back every shitty thing
you've said about her!
[JUNICHI] You're right!
I'm a loser virgin!
You can say whatever
you want about me,
but I'm not just gonna
let you get away
with bad-mouthing Yukana!
Yo! Where my boys?
You're gettin' a little
heated there, buddy.
So whadda ya say we take
this party outside?
[DAI laughs]
Hey, you're about to get your
ass kicked six ways to Sunday.
So, how does that make you feel?
I swear, I'm gonna make
you pay for what you said!
Heh.
It'll be fun just to see how
long you can keep that attitu--
Oh, man!
Check out the white knight
here pullin' a total bitch move!
Does your mama know
you borrowed her fist?
[laughs]
Coulda dodged that
with my eyes closed!
Ow! You bit me!
This son of a bitch
is actually biting me!
Uh! Get the fuck off me,
you stupid mutt!
I'm not letting go!
Not until you promise me
that you'll never go
near Yukana again!
You're insane!
Hey, assholes!
What're you waiting for?
Mess him up already!
[JUNICHI]
I can't give up.
Not unless he promises
to leave Yukana alone!
[DAI] Ow! Ow! Ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Get off of me!
Promise me!
Fine, whatever. I promise,
okay? I won't go near her.
[DAI]
You pathetic piece of shit!
Pud-pounding virgin!
Like I'd ever keep a promise
to a chump like you!
See, sluts like Yukana
do what they do
to get guys like me to use 'em
like a laundromat
washing machine.
Drop a load in 'em,
then walk away!
So that's what I'm gonna do!
It's what she wants!
Don't worry, man.
You can have my sloppy
seconds when I'm done.
[ALL chuckling]
[JUNICHI]
Damn it.
I won't let them near her.
No matter what happens to me.
[BRO C yells]
Huh? What's up your butt?
[chuckles]
Yo, that was mad ballsy,
Mister Virgin.
[groaning]
[BRO A]
Who the hell are you?
Ranko, holy crap.
Get lost, bitch!
[BRO D]
Take this, you dumb cu--
I know you.
Yeah, you were a year ahead
of us in middle school, right?
[DAI laughs]
Damn, girl, you got a pair
of tomatoes on you.
How 'bout I slip my cucumber
in there and make it a salad?
Wow, does that kind
of line ever work?
Heh. Guys, show this
uppity skank--
[BRO E yells]
[DAI growls]
Ah, come on, what now?
[GUYS chuckle]
We can't abide
assholes like you
who would dare raise their
hands against a woman.
We're gonna have to
make you pay for that!
Damn skippy!
Now let's see how you
like getting fisted, bro!
It makes me angry
when people hurt women.
And you wouldn't like
me when I'm angry.
[DAI groans]
[DAI]
Jeez, are there any more rats
waitin' to crawl
out of the woodwork?
Argh!
Junichi, you alive?
[JUNICHI]
Yeah.
[SHINPEI]
Don't you have somewhere else
you need to be right now?
Yeah, dude, you
don't have the time
to deal with these asshats.
Get outta here!
What are you waiting for?
Go to your lady.
Aw, you guys.
[SHINPEI chuckles]
Leave these deedle honks
to us. Now go, scram!
I'm glad you guys are
my friends. Even Minoru.
--[GUYS] You can do it!
--[JUNICHI] You're the best!
Silly virgin, you think I'm just
gonna let your ass get away.
[RANKO laughs]
There's a hot chick
standing in front of you,
but you'd rather
chase after him?
Fuck you all very much.
But you're all outta luck now
'cause we outnumber you.
'Kay, boys, have at 'em!
Rip their balls off!
[JUNICHI]
C'mon, pick up. Pick up.
[phone buzzing]
Uh, so, do you need to get that?
No, it's fine.
Who was that?
Was it Junichi calling?
Damn it. No answer.
Please show up.
[NENE sighs]
Let's face the facts,
Junichi's a loser.
Not to mention
selfish, unreliable,
and his breath smells
like cat food.
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
Listen, girl.
You can't let this boy
get away with anything.
Left to his own devices,
he'll go astray.
With him, you need to crack
the whip and take control.
Oh, really? You sure do
know a lot about Junichi.
No, it's not like that! Shut up!
Yeah? Why so defensive then?
Seems hella-suspect to me.
But whatever. I know
him better than anyone.
I thought I knew him.
But now, I-I don't know
where his head is at.
[YUKANA]
I mean, at this point,
I'm not sure if Junichi
even likes me still.
Girlfriend, this I
can say for sure.
That kid is hardcore in love
with you. Like, hardcore.
And like I said, I know
him better than anyone,
so you know I'm right.
Nene.
All right, tell me this.
Has he ever tried to tell you
how he feels about you?
Y'know, like, poured his heart
out to you or whatever?
And do you think that's really
how he feels about you?
Actually, I kinda
hope that it isn't.
Well then, you should
ask him again directly.
That way you'll know for sure
before you go crazy worrying.
Yui.
Both of you, thanks so much.
I'm not entirely
sure how I feel yet,
so I need to do some thinking,
but I will ask him again.
Hey, monster boobs,
isn't it colossally stupid
to help your love rival?
I could ask you the
same exact thing.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
[NENE giggles]
[BROS groaning]
[laughs]
Just give up already!
Okay, I'm done.
Whoa, you guys
are really strong.
Annoying as hell, but strong.
I promise you, I'll stay way
the hell away from you guys.
Please, just don't hurt me.
Ya really think we'd
believe anything
that comes outta your mouth?
Hmph.
[MANAMI] Hi there.
Why is that boy crying?
Did he get a boo-boo?
[MANAMI giggles]
Manami, over here!
[MANAMI wailing]
I hope it's all right if I put
my hand on your shoulder.
Please don't cry, darling.
Here.
You're an angel.
[DAI laughing]
You dumbasses! Like I'd
ever beg for mercy!
Suck my big, hairy balls!
Gee, mister. Thank you.
--[MINORU] Bye for now.
--Bye-bye.
[MINORU growling]
[MINORU] Bad man do bad
thing to little girl.
Make Minoru angry.
Uh, what now?
[MINORU roars]
[DAI screaming]
So should we try to stop him?
Uh, I guess? Maybe?
[DAI]
Help me, Mommy!
[SHINPEI] Somebody get
this guy some puppies!
Bring me some fucking puppies!
[laughs]
Oh, you know what?
I just realized the perfect
term to describe you.
Wanna take a guess what it is?
Please don't hurt me,
I'm begging you!
Ma-mah. Sorry.
It's not, "Please don't
hurt me, I'm begging you."
The answer we were looking
for was: "Nutless"!
Ow, my balls! My big,
beautiful balls!
[RANKO]
Listen up, douche nozzle,
'cause I want you to drill
this into that toxic wad
of body spray and pickup
artist tips you call a brain.
Fartholes like you who only
think of women as objects
for your pleasure are
better off without nuts.
Hey! Let the big guy go!
[MINORU grunting]
Uh, are you sure?
[laughs]
Do it, or you boys'll
end up nutless, too.
[KEIGO, SHINPEI]
Okay.
Me like kids. Me no like you!
In my experience, guys like you
always need to learn their
lesson the hard way.
[MINORU] Me like kids.
Me no like you!
[DAI screaming]
[JUNICHI] I sent her that
message a while ago,
but I have no idea if
she's gonna show up.
[JUNICHI] Oh, well.
Guess she's not coming.
No. I'll wait here
until she does.
[phone beeps]
Yukana?
What the hell have
they done now?
Well, I'm just glad
they're all okay.
[JUNICHI] Y'know, thinking back,
these last few months,
they've been like a dream.
[JUNICHI] It all started when I
got down on my hands and knees
and begged.
[JUNICHI] If I hadn't asked her
out, and she hadn't said yes,
then none of this
would've been possible.
[JUNICHI] Why am I being
such a puss about this?
It's time to show her
the man I can be.
Yukana!
'Kay, so, what did
you wanna say?
[JUNICHI]
Um, Yukana, would you please...
...go out with me?!
[YUKANA] I'm experiencing
some major déjà vu here,
and not in a good way.
I may look stupid,
but I can't give up now.
I'm an idiot, a fool,
and a pervert.
And, oh, yeah,
I'm a virgin, too!
All this time, I was only
thinking about myself.
I've been weak, and I
hurt you because of it.
I can't apologize
enough for that.
[YUKANA]
Huh. And?
[JUNICHI]
The first time I did this,
I just asked you out without
giving it much thought.
I barely even knew you, so
I didn't really have
any feelings for you,
for who you are.
I was only in it for
that sweet, sweet ass.
I know, I hate myself
right now, too.
But... that's changed.
I'm in love with
you now, Yukana.
I can't imagine my
life without you.
And I really don't want to.
What made you fall
in love with me?
[JUNICHI] I love how you're
so nice to everyone,
no matter who they are
or what kind of
day you're having.
I love how you smile
so innocently.
I even love that face you make
when I'm making stupid
pop culture references.
Yeah?
And I especially love
how you're so trusting
and always believe me.
I really, really, really,
really love that!
C'mon, get your head
outta the grass, Junichi.
How long are you planning
to stay down there?
Stand up.
[JUNICHI]
Okay.
B.T. dubs, why would you
ask me to go out with you?
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
You're already my
boyfriend, boyfriend.
Uh, yeah, I know
that, but still,
this time, I just
wanted to do it right.
Hey, so, are you
busy after this?
Hang on, lemme check.
Uh, nope. I'm free.
There's somewhere I
wanna go. With you.
I'd love to!
Awesome! Yay!
So where're we goin'?
That's for me to know,
and you to find out!
Oh, I've been meaning to ask,
why do you look so messed up?
[JUNICHI chuckles]
Oh, I was in such a hurry to
see you, I musta tripped.
Well, I was
gonna go change,
so you should go home
and change, too.
Yeah, good plan.
[YUKANA]
Junichi!
Hey there, boyfriend!
[JUNICHI]
Whoa. She looks like a model.
Wait, that dress looks
familiar. Isn't that--?
Ding, ding, ding!
It's the one you liked
that day at the mall!
[JUNICHI chuckles]
Well, so? You like it?
[JUNICHI]
It's super-cute!
And sexy as hell!
I think that it's perfect.
Y'know, for your body type.
Well, that's a decent enough
answer coming from you,
so I guess you pass, barely.
[JUNICHI chuckles]
So I just barely pass, huh?
You're a tough grader.
[YUKANA giggles]
Let's go!
An amusement park?
Remember? Huh? The beach?
You said you wanted to go to
an amusement park at night?
[JUNICHI]
Huh.
Yeah. I said that, huh?
[laughs]
[giggles]
Of course!
[JUNICHI] This is incredible!
She's so darn sweet!
How did I ever get so lucky?
I just wanna scream to the
world that she's my girlfriend
and I love her!
Can't wait to go on rides
with my ride-or-die!
[JUNICHI] Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
[YUKANA yells, laughs]
[YUKANA]
Come on, scaredy-cat.
[JUNICHI]
No, it's okay, I'm good.
I'll wait for you outside.
[ROBOT A]
Welcome to Hell, mortal.
That bitch got you good!
[JUNICHI]
Now this ride's more my spee--!
[JUNICHI sighs]
Someone's been
having too much fun.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
It's been so long since my last
time at an amusement park,
it all just feels so new again.
This is kinda nice, isn't it?
Almost feels like
an actual date.
Yeah. You're right.
Hey, Junichi. Come with me!
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
Ah! I knew they'd have one!
Look, Junichi, a photo booth!
'Kay.
[TEEN GIRL A]
Ooh, baby, I want the big one!
[JUNICHI] It's an
amusement park at night,
so of course it's
nothing but couples.
Y'know, it kinda
makes me nervous--
H-Hey, where did you go?
[JUNICHI]
There are so many photo booths.
Which one is she in?
[yelps]
Whoa. Sorry, wrong booth!
[JUNICHI]
They're taking a kissing photo?
Man, real-life
couples are gross.
Wait a tick. What if Yukana
wants to try that with me?
[YUKANA]
Can't show you that.
There you are, junichi.
I thought you were
right behind me,
but then you just ghosted.
You scared me.
Sorry.
[YUKANA giggles]
'Kay, let's take a pic.
[JUNICHI]
Uh, okay.
[VOICE A]
Get ready to swap some spit!
They encourage that?
[YUKANA laughs]
That is hilarious!
We could just do a normal one.
We don't have to do
what the computers say.
Aw, but that's so boring and
played out, don't'cha think?
C'mon, Junichi, let's do it!
A kiss pic.
[VOICE A] Okay, here
we go, lovers! Three...
[JUNICHI]
Are you sure?
[VOICE A]
...two, one!
[YUKANA laughs]
You should see your face!
I'm literally dead right now!
[laughs]
[JUNICHI] Damn it! She tricked
me and I fell for it!
Why am I so
freaking gullible?
[YUKANA gasps]
It's so pretty! Prance over
here and take a look!
Wow, jeez.
[YUKANA]
Here, this is for you.
Thanks. I guess?
[YUKANA]
Aren't we just adorbs?
Hashtag relationship goals!
[JUNICHI chuckles]
Well, I'm happy it
makes you happy.
Tonight was fun, right?
[JUNICHI]
Yeah, super fun.
So thanks. I'm really glad
that you brought me here.
'Course!
Y'know, it's cool hanging
out with the whole gang,
but hanging out on
our own is nice, too.
Don't you think?
Let's come back here!
The same day next year,
and the year after that.
And then, every year after.
Yeah. It's a date.
Hey, so can I ask you something?
What is it you see in me
and why do you believe
in me so much?
I mean, after all the terrible
things I've said and done.
I'd tell you,
but then I'd have to kill you.
Oh. That's nice.
'Kay, bye-bye!
[JUNICHI screams]
[YUI]
Good morning, Junichi.
Oh, hey there, Yui.
Hey, wait, before you go!
I wanted to thank
you for listening
to my problems the other day.
You helped me figure out
a lot of things up there.
There's no need to thank me.
I was just dishing out my
honest opinion, that's all.
No big deal.
If that somehow helped you
to solve a problem, well,
then you did the heavy lifting
all on your own, Junichi.
If you say so.
Oh, hey, I almost forgot to ask.
Are you into live
streaming at all?
[gasps]
Uh. Streaming? Don't
even know what that is.
Oh, well, there's this girl
who kinda looks like you
and I thought that maybe...
Nope! I've never even
heard of Mistress Boa.
[NENE]
Junichi! Guess who!
Nene, you're getting
too top-heavy for this!
What? Never!
[NENE]
Ooh.
Your face. It's looking
all handsome again.
Huh? Is that so?
Mh-hm. Yup, back to normal!
Uh, I guess that's good?
[RANKO]
Lucky you, Mister Virgin,
starting off your day with
all these girls around you.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, Ranko! And Yukana!
Good Morning, boyfriend.
Whoa. Something happened
between you two, didn't it?!
[NENE whines]
Seriously? You mean
just since yesterday?
[RANKO laughs]
Yeah, but you're still
a virgin, though, right?
'Cause if you're not, it's
bye-bye handsome giraffe.
Still a virgin.
Let's jet!
[YUI] Hey, they're
making a break for it!
[NENE]
Don't let 'em get away!
[GUYS]
This was truly a happy ending.
[AYUMI]
Yo, Ayumi here!
[KOKORO]
And Kokoro!
[AYUMI] Gah! It's all
over! The show's over!
[KOKORO]
Yep, totes over.
[AYUMI]
How are you so calm about this?
[KOKORO]
What do you mean?
[AYUMI] The season ended
without us getting
any major screen time!
[KOKORO]
Oh, yeah, right. That sucks!
[AYUMI] I told everyone
I was gonna be on TV!
[KOKORO]
Nobody else truly understands
our suffering, do they?
[AYUMI] Well, there's no
use bitching about it now!
[KOKORO] That's right!
[AYUMI, KOKORO]
See ya guys later! 'Kay, bye!