Yukana Yame, long time!
Wait, Dai?
When was the last time we saw
each other? Years, right?
Far too long if you ask me.
Damn, I've missed you.
And you have really
filled out that body
since last time we
got our hang on.
So sweet.
I'm surprised I was even
able to recognize you
with your new look.
You dyed your hair!
Heh.
I guess I was pretty lame
in our middle school days.
But I should be dope enough
to hook up with you now.
Whoa, Dai, coming
on strong much?
I don't remember you talking
this way. Someone's changed.
Uh. Oh, well.
I still would love for you to
come with me to lunch tomorrow.
Our old crew will be there.
Seriously?
I'm in! Let's get
our reminisce on!
Great. I'll spread the word.
[YUKANA]
Awesome!
[JUNICHI] What the hell?
He's a total Chad!
Ripped body. Alpha hair.
Probably ten inches soft!
He's got Yukana in
the palm of his hand.
And I-I don't wanna
be here anymore.
That's it.
I'll pretend I'm a useless lump
and just sink into the ground.
[DAI] They're gonna be
jacked to the tits.
[YUKANA] I haven't seen
most of them in forever!
In real life.
We Snap all the time.
[DAI] Man, Yukana,
you are such a hottie now.
You're gonna blow their minds.
You might even
blow more than that.
Wait, hold on. Who's that
weird dude with you?
Who?
It's just my boyfriend.
Junichi, I forgot
to introduce you.
That guy is Dai. We went to
middle school together.
Uh, what's up, bro?
I'm Junichi Hashiba. Yeah.
Call me Dai.
Nice to meet ya, June-y.
So you settled on a
nice guy, huh, Yukana?
I woulda thought with those
boobs you'd be way pickier.
[JUNICHI]
Speaking of boobs.
All right, enough
about the past!
You're embarrassing me
in front of my boyfriend!
Let's go, Junichi.
Bye! I'll see you
at lunch tomorrow!
[DAI]
Mm!
Oh my God, wasn't
that trip so fun?
Let's do one again next
year. Maybe we can...
[JUNICHI] It seems like
Yukana and that Dai guy
have kind of a past.
They're pretty friendly.
Oh, God, no! Did they date?
Think of me as an explorer.
Feeling my way through the
steamy undergrowth to love.
What happens when you
finally get to that love?
I drink from its essence.
Now, you must reveal your
fertile oasis to me, my peach.
[JUNICHI screams]
[JUNICHI]
Gross! Gross! Gross!
What's wrong? Junichi!
Nothing.
Sometimes you just gotta get the
bad thoughts out of your head.
Can you be less
"spazzy" and "weird"
and more "normal"
and "boyfriend"?
There.
[JUNICHI] After I
head-butted that light pole,
she still likes me.
Maybe there isn't
really anything
between her and
Chad Bonerschnitzle.
Unless, she's only
acting this way
so I don't get suspicious
and dig for dirt!
So wanna tell what's wrong?
Uh, well.
That old friend you bumped into
seemed really handsome.
What? You mean, Dai?
His hair's better,
and he dresses better.
He's taller, with
better facial symmetry.
It's like he walked right off
the page of a girls' manga,
or a set of a gay porn.
Oh, God, there's nothing to be
jealous about, Junichi, c'mon.
But I can't beat that
guy by any standard.
When you two talked,
it felt like you were
meant for each other
and I should be somewhere else.
Hey, don't say that.
That's not true at all.
And you got along so well, too.
I even got the vibe you
were a little embarrassed
introducing me to him
as your current boyfriend.
So you don't trust
me, is that it?
No.
Maybe.
Fine. Whatever. I'm going home.
So I just got back
from vacation,
and it was next-level bonkers!
Fun in the sun!
All my friends at the hot
springs had ginormous boobs!
Like, they're way
bigger than mine!
It was so embarrassing!
Wah! Wah!
[JUNICHI]
That's a weird coincidence.
I wonder if Boa is... Nah.
Holy balls. That
trip kicked ass!
I swear to God, guys,
ever since we've been home,
I haven't stopped jerking off.
Yeah, and those
cuties in floaties.
A shark wasn't the only
predator out there!
It's crazy!
Who'd ever think we'd get
to go on a beach trip
with willing females?
And we owe it all to this
fun-loving, happy guy here!
[JUNICHI sighs]
[JUNICHI]
No problem.
Uh, what's wrong?
You don't sound happy for a man
who was just on the beach
with top-shelf poon.
I'm very happy. Why do you ask?
Bro, I'm your best
friend and mentor.
If something's got you down,
then it's got me down, too.
So, come on, tell
me what's wrong
and I'll help you out.
[JUNICHI]
Okay.
So, um, this guy...
That asshole.
[KEIGO] This dude's bad
news for your balls.
[JUNICHI]
No, it's not a good situation.
[MINORU] Well, look,
worse-comes-to-worst,
you let her go ride him and
you hang with us again.
You can help me make
my maps of little kid--
[SHINPEI]
Junichi!
This is not N.T.R.! Netorare .
[JUNICHI]
Uh. What's " netorare "?
It's hentai. Cuck
porn to be exact.
[JUNICHI]
And what is "cuck"?
What you become when a man
takes your lover for himself,
and then ravages her sexually,
often right in front of you.
It's a shortening of the old
English word, "cuckold."
[JUNICHI]
What? "Cuckold"?
Wait a second, Junichi,
are you saying you
don't understand
any of the memes I send you?
Anyway, cuckoldry's
a fact of life,
which explains its enduring
popularity in amateur porn.
How is that popular?
It sounds awful!
Getting cheated on sucks!
Ooh!
I can tell by your tone
that you're turned on
by the humiliation that
comes with getting cucked.
[JUNICHI]
Dude, what the hell? No!
Barely three lines
ago, you said,
"Getting cheated on sucks."
That mix of dominance
and degradation
gives cuckoldry it's spice.
[JUNICHI]
That barely makes sense.
You idiot!
When a chick says "I don't like
butt stuff, but it feels good,"
that means she doesn't
want to like it.
Even though she
actually likes it!
Will you stop poking
me in the face?
All that and you
still don't get it?
[JUNICHI]
I'm more confused than ever.
There is one other thing
I need to warn him about.
I'm afraid Yukana's
new alpha-Chad suitor
is packin' a huge left
handed banjo in his pants!
And by "left handed banjo"
I assume you're referring
to his penis size.
Yes, his penis is very large.
As soon as it enters her,
it'll cast a spell.
Oh, I get it!
I'm never asking
for your help again!
[YUKANA]
What's up, ladies?
--Hey, you!
--Oh, hey, Yukana.
Well, Junichi.
You gotta figure out whether
she really likes you
'cause once Dai's deedle honk
goes in, you're cucked.
[JUNICHI]
I don't know what to do!
[YUKANA]
And then I just walked away!
--What? Really!
--Yukana.
Yeah, really!
You're like all feminist
now. It's so cute!
[JUNICHI]
She won't even look at me.
[JUNICHI] School's almost
over and I haven't said
one word to my girlfriend yet.
[JUNICHI] As soon as that
bell rings, it's go-time.
[bell ringing]
[JUNICHI]
Hey, uh--
Yakuza!
[JUNICHI] Yakuza? I can't
even get her name right!
Yeah?
I was thinking, maybe
we could walk home?
Yeah, I've got that thing
with my middle school
friends today.
Oh. Right. That.
Yeah. So, about yesterday--
[YUKANA] You'll have to
tell me later. I gotta go.
[JUNICHI]
Uh. Wait!
She's going off to cuck me!
[GUYS laughing]
♪ [ Love the pussy, love the
pussy, love the poo-say. ♪
♪ I get more pussy than a CPA. ♪
♪ I stroke it, I poke it.
Oops, I broke it! ♪
♪ 'Caused it to leak
like a broken faucet. ♪
♪ Hold up now, while I deposit ♪
♪ my one-eyed monster in
your skin closet... ♪
I'm sorry, bro.
She's out there
getting deedle honked
while you're in here sulking.
Aw, come on, Junichi.
Grab that microphone and
sing all your pain away!
Oh, my sweet Yukana!
Why has somebody trapped
you in this box?
You cuck!
Where am I?
You've come back to us.
Now listen up!
Tomorrow, there's something you
absolutely must do, all right?
[JUNICHI]
I'm not doing anything.
Oh, yes you are!
You're gonna forget
everything I said
about cucks and flesh muskets,
and go grovel to Yukana!
[JUNICHI]
I'm not sure what I did wrong.
[SHINPEI]
None of that matters.
You're a desperate man, Junichi.
You wanna keep this girl?
You want her love?
You grovel!
You eat that shit sandwich.
But it might be too late.
Like you said, she's
already under the spell
of his gigantic deedle honk.
It's all a waste of time.
Just eat it.
I said no.
It's just a metaphore.
--But--
--Just try it!
[JUNICHI] I--
Take a bite!
Fine, I'll try!
[SHINPEI]
Awesome!
And the best part is
that begging forgiveness
is a guaranteed panty-dropper!
Or so I've heard.
Wait, that doesn't
sound like a thing.
But I can see your point.
And with that "Chad" back in
her life, can't hurt to try.
Now try this. It's only the
best anime theme song ever.
You got that right.
[ALL] ♪ And no matter what,
we won't be apart. ♪
♪ That's because you
saved my heart. ♪
Yeah. That hit the spot.
Good times.
Well, it sure beats arguing
on Reddit all night.
Well, thanks, you
really cheered me up.
And you're ready
to start chompin'
on a big doodoo sammy, right?
She already thinks I'm
weak and desperate,
so I'm gonna lean into it more!
We should totally make
karaoke night our thing!
Wow. Ice cold.
[SHINPEI]
Well, that's the end of that.
Tch. That's why you won't
catch me dating older girls.
Junichi? How you
holdin' up, bud?
[SPIRIT laughing]
[SPIRIT] Junichi Hashiba will
return in the Next Life.
[SHINPEI] In a world where
Junichi is a total pant-stain.
[sighs]
[JUNICHI] I guess Yukana really
has been messing with me
all this time.
[JUNICHI]
Well, on the bright side,
it's nice to know a gut
feeling was actually right.
So now my life just goes back
to how it was pre-Yukana.
Sad. Lonely. Virginal.
Oh, wow.
I really do have some
serious feelings for her.
[YUKANA]
Yo!
Junichi, hey!
Oh, hey, hi.
Well, don't you look frazzled!
I'm guessing you
were up all night
thinking about what you did.
[JUNICHI] I can't exactly
think about what I did wrong
if I'm still confused about
what it is I did wrong.
Besides, you've done
way more wrong to me.
You cheated!
And now you're pretending
like everything's fine!
As for me, well, I thought it
over and decided I was a prob'ly
a little too cold
to you yesterday.
But if it made you reflect,
maybe the tough love
was worth it, after all.
Yesterday.
Huh? What about yesterday?
What did you do after school?
I already told you.
I met up with Dai and my other
old friends from middle school.
[JUNICHI]
I saw you.
I saw you and Dai
canoodling in that café
like you were on the
hottest date ever.
[YUKANA]
What?
If you were there,
you should've come over.
Why was it just the
two of you alone?
Well, the party broke up,
but he said he still had
something to tell me,
one-on-one, so I listened.
[JUNICHI]
She's lying.
They probably even
rehearsed that story.
That's why she answered so fast.
[JUNICHI]
Was it fun?
I bet it was a blast
playing mind games
with a dorky virgin.
Well, guess what? You won.
You fucked up my heart more
than you ever could've wanted.
So just take your "win"
and get out of my life!
Gah, it hurts!
If I'm going to feel like this
whenever I start to
think about you...
...I'll be a virgin forever!
[JUNICHI]
I don't get it.
What's with that
look she gave me?
[YUI]
Junichi?
Do you have a moment?
[YUI]
Junichi.
If something's going on
with you and Yukana,
well, I'm here if you
need a friendly ear
to listen to your problems.
I don't understand why she's
even doing this to me.
[YUI]
Doing what?
Dating someone like me
in the first place.
[YUI] Sounds like you
have this on-going fear
that Yukana's feelings might
not be all that sincere.
Yeah, it's like our
relationship is a big prank.
'Cause, otherwise, nothing
about it makes any sense.
[YUI] Junichi, you
really feel this way?
It all makes sense to me now.
Yukana's a terrible person
who's only been pretending
to like me in order to hurt me.
But on the bright side,
I learned a lot from
this awful experience.
Now I know to never get close
to or trust a woman again.
[YUI]
All right, enough!
I was wrong about you.
One bad relationship, and what,
you decide to become a monk?
What about all the other
girls in the world?
I feel bad for me! I mean them!
I thought you were different,
but you're a typical
selfish guy.
Screw you, Junichi!
You're not even worthy
to be my servant!
[sighs]
Oh, boy.
[NENE]
Junichi!
What's wrong, bub?
You're walking around
like Charlie Brown!
Nah, nothing's wrong.
Yeah, right!
Whenever you smile like that
and say, "Oh, it's nothing,"
you're really saying,
"it's something."
I can't hide
anything from you.
[NENE] Well, I've only known you
your whole life, ya big boner.
Now, c'mon, tell me
what's going down!
Fine, here goes.
[NENE]
Hmm.
Well, I'd normally give
you some sound advice,
but I'm all out!
[NENE]
Boop.
Look, don't mope around over
something so small, okay?
Otherwise, you'll--
Go on. I'll what?
Otherwise, you'll end up
having to marry me.
Don't you remember your promise?
Why would that
make me marry you?
Because if you're moping,
then you're not cool!
Wow, you're really
thinking far out.
How 'bout this?
If we grow up, and I'm like,
a huge dork who
can't get any babes,
then I'll marry you!
[JUNICHI]
Yukana cheats and lies about it.
Yui says I'm self-centered.
And now, Nene says I'm not cool.
Quite the fun day I had.
[YUI]
What's been going on with me?
Well, I liked this
one boy until today.
But now his
super-clueless response
has got me all bummed out.
And I'm not just
depressed, either.
This guy's got me legit angry.
So, rewind: Boy-crush
has this girlfriend
and I try not to fall for him.
Y'know, outta respect.
But then today, things were bad
with them, and I made my move.
Tell him how I feel.
But he didn't get it.
Only thing he cared
about was himself.
He pisses me off!
I'm actually friends with the
girl he's still maybe-dating.
It's really hard, y'know?
He's bad talking to girls,
and he's a-a virgin.
And he's really not
cool, like at all.
But he's always been nice to me.
It happened so fast.
First I'm crushing on him,
and the next thing y'know,
I'm falling for him.
That's why I need him
to act how he used to,
so he can take his rightful
spot as my servant!
[NENE] You wanted to meet
just to talk about Junichi?
That's right. He, uh...
Uh...
Um, I don't know. I--
It's just...
Sorry, Yukana, you can
text me the story later.
Wait, Ranko,
where are you going?
[RANKO] Sorry, ladies, I have
business to take care of.
Mister Virgin knows what happens
whenever he makes my Yukana cry.
Is it weird if I
order a sandwich?
[JUNICHI]
How would you guys describe me?
A virgin cuck.
A virgin dork.
A virgin perv.
[laughs]
[JUNICHI]
Why'd I ask?
I see you've given up on life.
That would explain why you're
letting us dog you so hard, huh.
[RANKO]
Hey! Virgin!
[GUYS chattering]
I warned you about
making her cry
and now you're
gonna pay the price!
Ranko, you're so pretty
when you're angry.
[RANKO]
I know you don't believe me,
but Yukana always puts
your feelings first.
Even when she goes out with
friends, at the end of the day,
she's still coming back to
your dumb ass, Junichi!
Yukana.
But, no.
You just had to confront
her like a paranoid-psycho.
[JUNICHI]
You're right.
I'm just a dumb,
needy, loser virgin.
I'm also selfish and entitled.
[RANKO]
And?
That's why--
That's why despite everything I
just said being painfully true,
I'm going to tell her.
She's my girl! And no
other guy's taking her!
Well, you just walked
a thin line, son.
Much more romantic
than possessive.
So then, does that mean
you're not gonna beat me up?
[RANKO]
Yep.
Though think of this more
as a temporary truce
than me accepting you
two as a couple.
[DAI]
Heh. Let's eat!
[BROS chattering]
Whoa. This gal Dai found
is totally steak sauce.
Yeah, I'd like to bend her
over the hood of my Mustang.
Man, this Yukana Yame.
She's a Tokyo Ten.
[DAI chuckles]
I know, brah! Gals are the
easiest pieces to land.
After everyone left,
I just whispered
that I had something
important to tell her
and she leaned right in.
[ALL laughing]
So, yeah. We can
go out. Boyfriend.
I plow through girlfriends
and leave a trail of
cucks in my wake.
[YUKANA]
Hey, I had fun today.
Next time, you might
even be my first choice
for a karaoke partner.
[giggles]
After I take her
to the bone zone,
I'll let you guys
blast her, too.
Slunts like this one
need lots of vitamin D.
[YUKANA] So what's your
idea of the perfect date
if you could do anything
in the world?
Sexist pigs!
Condoms are for boys.
I just finish on her belly.
[BRO D laughs]
[AYUMI]
Hey, guys, Ayumi here!
[KOKORO]
And Kokoro!
[YUKANA] You're so different
here compared to class.
[AYUMI] What? How would
anyone be able to tell?
[KOKORO]
Yeah, viewers barely know you
when you're only on
every third episode!
[YUKANA]
Viewers?
[KOKORO]
Stars only focus on themselves!
[AYUMI] We might as well just be
background extras to you, huh?
[YUKANA] I don't get it,
but we'll always be friends.
[AYUMI, KOKORO]
Give us screentime!
[YUKANA]
But the next one's the last.
[AYUMI, KOKORO]
Dammit!