[chuckles]
That tickles.
[YUKANA] Junichi, I know you
boys get hard in the morning,
but why does this one feel
like it could cut a diamond?
Well, babe, I'm gonna
guess it's because
your crotch is grinding on me?
Yep, that's why.
So you... like it?
I-I must touch your boobies!
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
[screams]
Hey!
[NENE]
What?
[JUNICHI] Calm down, Junichi.
Try to understand.
You woke up in the dark
to find a mysterious girl,
whose face you can't see,
but whose giant boobs you can
definitely feel and-- Oh, God.
Rockets on deck!
[JUNICHI yelling]
Seriously, who are you?
And what're you doing
breaking into my room?
[NENE coughs]
Yeah, so. It's all like--
Like, you're my bae.
But I get the vibe that
I'm not your bae, Junichi.
I'm just some ho.
I'm not totally butt-hurt,
but I'm partially butt-hurt.
I'm, like, butt sore.
[JUNICHI] I don't have the
faintest idea what the hell
this girl's talking about!
What?
All that talk and you still
can't figure out who I am?
Forget being butt-hurt, you've
made me hella-pissed off!
And that's, like, way worse!
[JUNICHI] Yeah, no. I still
don't know who you are.
What? You really don't recognize
me, even in the light?
Fine.
Hey.
After causing all that drama,
you're just gonna ignore me?
And why should I wait for you
when I got Snaps to chat?
This gal ain't got time for
a boy who won't grind!
Uh, yeah.
I don't know who you are,
and to be honest,
I'm not sure I even understand
what you're saying.
It's a whole lot of slang.
Now, do you mind?
Please get off my junk.
[NENE] Could it be that my
"gal-speak" still needs work?
No, that can't be it.
I've been rehearsing for
this moment all week.
The problem is that
Junichi just woke up
and isn't thinking straight.
I'll wait till later.
He'll come around by then.
No, you worked far too
hard to look adorable
for right here and now!
Junichi, it's me, Nene, you see?
[JUNICHI]
Hm?
[chuckles]
Ah, Nene! That's
you under there?
At least it makes sense, then,
for you to be sneaking
into my bedroom.
Wait, no it doesn't!
Nene, you've changed!
[giggles]
Hey. Uh, Nene?
You mind letting go of me?
When we were little kids,
we used to walk to school
every day like this.
But now we're all grown
up in high school.
If people see me
walking arm-in-arm
with my childhood friend,
they'll get the wrong idea.
Especially the cool kids,
I don't want them to see
us, that'll be, awful.
[SHINPEI]
Yo!
[JUNICHI]
Ahh! Shit!
Hey, we're just walking, yeah.
Right, "walking."
Nice day. Eh, Junichi?
[MINORU grunts]
What is this pretty young thing?
Does your-Does your
dolly have a name?
[JUNICHI]
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Hey, you guys're
Junichi's buddies, right?
I saw you the other
day in class,
but I don't think we
had a chance to meet.
I'm the girl next door, Nene!
A lot of people think I'm
still in elementary school
because I'm so short,
but I'm just a year
younger than you guys.
Ugh. I'll pass, grandma.
I'm not wasting my
time on someone
who's already started puberty
and got hair in all
the wrong places.
[laughs]
Oh, Junichi, I didn't know
your friends were so funny!
That's Minoru.
He'll be going door to
door introducing himself
to all his neighbors soon.
He's dead inside.
Not only does that cute
gal like ya, Junichi,
your oddly proportioned
childhood friend
has begun dressing up like
the other girl you're dating
in a brazen attempt to
ride your piss weasel.
Why do they all like you?
Don't you realize how sexually
frustrated I am? Jerk!
C'mon, pal. You've got
enough poon for a lifetime.
Give some to your
friends in need!
[JUNICHI yells]
Back up, you creeps!
I know it looks like I'm
dating another girl.
But just because I'm
arm-in-arm with an old friend
doesn't mean
anything's going on!
Yeah.
There's nothing
scandalous about me
walking to school with
Junichi like this.
The two of us are
just, like, y'know?
Really, really, really
close friends!
Um, please stop.
When you hold on
to me like that,
your giant boobs rub
against my forearm!
[BOTH wheeze]
That's part of the fun!
[SHINPEI]
Ah! I gotta go home and fist it!
Oh, God, runnin'
with a boner hurts!
I better go. Enjoy grandma.
Uh, why do they always
freak out like that?
Well, like the one guy
said, they're jealous.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, hey, Yui.
Good morning, Junichi Hashiba.
Oh, thanks. And a
good morning to you.
[JUNICHI] So many things
from the last few days
still don't make sense.
But I'm pretty sure she
asked me out, right?
Sorry about the other day.
I'd really love it if, well,
you don't tell anyone
about me asking you out.
Yeah. No problem.
I never gossip about that stuff.
Smart move, Hashiba.
Oh, good. Happy to
keep things smooth.
[YUI]
Everything's back to normal.
That's weird. He smells
like another girl.
[NENE]
Oh, good, there you are!
I almost forgot to say:
Today, we're also
walking home together!
[YUI]
It's her scent that's on him!
Well, I already told Yukana
I'd do something with
her after school.
[NENE] Aww! But I wanna be
with you today! It's my turn!
[YUI] Who the hell is this
pair of tits on toothpicks
trying to take my man?
[NENE]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Junichi, I can't help but
notice that this girl
is getting rather angry.
Maybe it's 'cause I
took away her chance
to be alone with you?
[NENE laughs]
Take him. He's all yours, sista.
Last thing I wanna do is make a
fellow gal get hella-pissed off.
Wow. I wonder if I'll look
like her when I'm that age.
I definitely want her hair,
but not the wrinkles.
Right, Junichi?
Settle down, Nene.
'Kay? That sounds rude!
I love how she
carries herself, too.
She's like a 30-year-old cougar
still going to high school.
It's great.
[laughs]
Big mistake.
No one has ever insulted
me as much as you
and lived to tell about it.
[JUNICHI] Oh no, what
have you done, Nene?
[STUDENT A]
Yui! Class is about to start!
'Kay, I'll be right there!
[JUNICHI groaning]
What a bitch. Are you okay?
Uh. Is every day gonna
be like this from now on?
[JUNICHI] I swear, if one more
girl comes up to me today,
I'm going to lose my mind.
[YUKANA]
Junichi!
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
Hey, boyfriend,
you look tired A-F!
Oh. Hey, Yukana.
You sound even worse than
you look. What's going on?
Just too many frustrating
things happening to me, lately,
and I don't understand why.
Aw. High school
drama. I feel ya.
[JUNICHI chuckles]
That's it!
I'm gonna take you
someplace fun this weekend
that I guarantee will put a
smile back on that frowny face!
Yeah. Sure. Sounds great!
[YUKANA giggles]
Don't worry, you'll
have a blast there.
So what is this place?
And what, ruin the surprise?
You're just gonna hafta wait.
[SHINPEI]
I can't believe it!
He's got multiple girls
spreading their legs for him,
while we sit here
with dry dicks!
Too bad we can't re-load life
from an earlier save point.
Don't get too
worked up over him.
The key to being happy in life
is to only worry
about the things
you have direct control over.
Like for me, it's my new
cartography hobby!
Maps of where all the
little girls live in town,
complete with their
parents' work schedules.
Pretty cool, huh?
My God. Hear yourself.
I hope in the near future
men in uniforms come
to take you away.
When you get your one phone
call, don't bother calling us.
[MINORU]
Want me to text?
I want you to stop.
[YUKANA]
I'm taking this!
[JUNICHI]
Hey!
I was more excited to
eat that pot sticker
than you might think.
It's your fault for keeping
it on the plate so long.
Come on, I'll give you
some of my melon bread
if you quit acting
all butt-hurt.
Eat!
Taste good?
[JUNICHI]
Yeah, it's really pretty good.
Hey, talking with your
mouth full is so rude!
And now, we're even
for the pot sticker!
What? No fair!
[JUNICHI] One day I'm going
to show her my big potsticker!
[RANKO] Don't get your hopes
up too high, Mister Virgin.
'Cause I will kill your giraffe.
[RANKO chuckles]
What? What are you
talking about?
Inside joke.
When are you gonna give me
a taste of what you got?
It looks so moist.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, man.
I forgot all about Ranko
being a jealous psycho!
Why's life so complicated?
[RANKO] I won't even let you
flirt with her when I'm around.
[NENE]
Junichi? Oh, there you are!
I got like hella-mad
searching the school
for my favorite boy-toy Junichi!
But now that I finally found
him, I'm hella-happy!
[NENE laughs]
Whoa, watch it, there, Nene.
What'd I say about grabbing me?
Unless it's an emergency.
Is it?
Well, kind of!
I made you cookies!
Here! Open wide!
Uh, no. I'm good. Thanks.
Wow! Your last snack is
still on your cheek!
Hey! That's gross!
All I can taste is you!
Hey.
How come I haven't
gotten a chance
to kiss you on the cheek yet?
[JUNICHI] Oh, yeah, this
day just keeps on giving!
What man wouldn't like a
clingy female friend to say,
"Hey, I baked you cookies!"
and then proceed to lick
bread crumbs off your cheek
in front of your girlfriend?
[laughing]
Mister Virgin, who's
Tits McGuillicutty?
[JUNICHI]
This is bad. Very, very bad.
You can't cheat, Junichi.
'Cause we're through!
No! Don't go!
I wasn't cheating
on you, I swear!
This is what you get
for making Yukana cry!
[YUKANA]
German Suplex!
Spinning Toehold!
By God Almighty, that's
a Cripple Crossface!
Somebody stop the dang match!
Ranko Honjou is
your new champion!
[RANKO yells]
This is, uh...
Yeah? This is what?
Hey! I knew I recognized
you from somewhere!
We met after school the other
day by the front gate, right?
You splurged on a
makeover since then,
and it threw me for a loopsie.
You're Junichi's kid sister.
No, we're not related.
Well, Yukana and this
half-assed gal have a history.
Not really.
It's just hard to forget meeting
someone who's so small and cute.
I totes forgot to introduce
myself to you the other day.
My name's Yukana.
I'm his girlfriend.
So you weren't joking the
other day about dating him?
I am hella-pissed right now,
you bae-sealing, b-to-the-itch!
That is like, so, 2008.
You talk really weird,
you know that? Love it!
[NENE] What? Am I still
not sounding like a gal?
No, that's crazy.
My impression is flawless!
Yukana is just trying
to get in my head
because she's worried
I'll steal Junichi away
with my superior gal-ness!
But to be safe,
I better find something I have
that clearly beats her.
Boobs.
Do you mind kneeling down a sec?
Is this okay?
[JUNICHI]
Oh my God, it's too much!
The elephant in the room
is definitely going
to break through my pants!
So I think it's pretty
clear that mine are bigger!
Yeah!
Your boobs are clearly bigger
than mine, no argument here.
Ranko, look!
Get on down here.
[RANKO laughs]
She's right. You're a half-assed
gal with full boobs.
I thought mine were big,
but next to yours, they're
mosquito nibbles.
[YUKANA]
Easy, Ranko.
My nips are hard.
[JUNICHI screams]
[JUNICHI]
War. Why does Man fight?
Are there good reasons
for one nation
to ever wage war
against another?
Some might say resources,
or politics, or religion.
But those people
would all be stupid.
Because there's no
good reason to fight
so long as beauty
remains in the world.
[JUNICHI]
Hallelujah!
[JUNICHI] These three
goddesses are pressing
their chests against each other.
The sight of it alone should
be enough to rid the world
of all hate and conflict!
Boobs're great.
[NENE] Hold on. Are they
seriously enjoying this?
It's really creepy.
What? Why'd you stop?
You don't really care about
Junichi, you're just using him!
You'll kick him to the
curb as soon as you meet
a more experienced guy.
I mean, there's no
reason to date a virgin.
You're just messing
with his head!
For a cute girl, you
really twist the knife.
Why's that?
[NENE]
Why's that what?
Why is it you think Junichi
can't get a girl
to fall for him?
Because...
I've known him for years.
Longer than you two,
or any other girls at school
have, that's for sure!
I get that Junichi's not
exactly Mister Popularity,
but still, that didn't stop me
from wanting to
become his girlfriend.
There's a lotta good
things about him.
You know that, right?
Even better than me, I bet.
[NENE]
I--
Um, you don't have to cry.
Kiss my eye, you big dummies!
Have you ever been called
a "dummy" before?
She's cute. So it's fine.
Poor Nene. Now what?
[YUI] I'm sorry for not being
my normal, playful self, guys,
but I had a bad day.
Let's just say...
Nene's a gal. It's so strange.
I better learn more
about how gals think
before I get blindsided again.
Don't forget to click on
the link below and donate!
Anyway, this stupid,
monster-boobed underclassman
made a crack about
me looking old.
"A monster-boobed
underclassman"?
Oh, boy.
I haven't heard from Nene
since then. Hope she's good.
[JUNICHI snoring]
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
I'm back.
Uh. Nene, is that you?
Oh. How ya doin'?
Been a few hours.
Whoa, holy crap, Nene!
Are you completely naked?
Nene, stop!
[JUNICHI]
They're soft and huge.
Junichi. I think it's
time that we... make love.
[JUNICHI wheezes]
You wanna have sex with me?
[JUNICHI] I feel every part
of her against my skin.
Now go turn this
half-assed gal
into a grown-ass woman.
[JUNICHI]
All right, be cool.
Again, it's important that you
calmly take stock of things.
You woke up, and for the
second night in a row,
your childhood friend is
naked and grinding on you!
How the hell am I supposed
to calmly do anything?
[JUNICHI yelps]
[roaring]
W-Wait a minute.
Don't rush into this!
[LIBIDO laughs]
[LIBIDO] I'm stronger
and harder than ever!
And I'm parking my pigskin
bus in her muffin shop!
[COOL]
Don't do anything stupid.
Listen. We grew up
alongside Nene.
She might as well be our sister.
[LIBIDO laughs]
[JUNICHI] You can't Charlie
Bravo the embodiment of cock!
Ha. You're not strong
at all, you're pathetic.
Drowning in your lust.
But there's another way.
A better path for all of us!
Fusion Love!
[LIBIDO]
What in the hell?
[BOTH] Wow! That's it!
The better path to love!
Heh.
I stand now above
all selfish lust!
[LIBIDO]
What's that you're sayin?!
It's over.
The end of your
obsession with sex.
You have my sympathies, though.
You wont feel a thing.
[LIBIDO] And I promise you
there's no part of Junichi
that can stop me now!
Oh, ballz.
[BOTH]
Yay, go me!
[FUSION] Those who burn twice
as bright, burn half as long,
and now, old friend,
it's time I light your wick!
Hah!
[LIBIDO] No, no, stop it!
Ow! Wow, that feels great!
[FUSION] His was a path any
of us could've fallen on.
Had I been consumed
by carnal desire,
it would've been you
having to erase me.
Well, gentlemen.
What's our goal when
it comes to sex?
Oh, I know this one!
Of course, I know it!
[ALL] Yukana will be the first
woman to take our seed!
Sorry.
I can't do it.
But why?
Why's it so hard to convince
you that I love you?
[JUNICHI]
That's why I won't do it.
I don't feel the same way
so I'd just be taking
advantage of your feelings.
You're a boy,
why do you even care?
Junichi, I want you
as my first, so do me!
[JUNICHI]
Mh-mh.
I'm sorry, no.
Besides, if I have sex with you,
I'd also be hurting Yukana.
Guess what.
When we're all grown up,
you're gonna be my husband!
Wow, you're really
thinking far out.
How about this?
If we grow up, and I'm like,
a huge dork who can't
get any babes,
then I'll marry you!
Nene.
Well, Junichi, you didn't grow
up to be a dork, after all.
Huh?
[YUKANA]
And what're you thinking about
on this delicious morning?
Ha!
What's up, Yukana?
You're still sad?
You used to be all funny
and now you're all not.
Well, if you're not gonna
tell me what's wrong,
I'll squeeze it out of ya!
[laughs]
Much better! I just want
you to be yourself again!
[JUNICHI] I think that's
her way of showing
she's worried about me.
[NENE]
Hey, move it!
Get away from my Junichi!
Uh. Nene?
Morning, cutie.
So, I've decided!
Uh, you what?
[NENE laughs]
I've decided to become an
even cooler gal than Yukana,
so that way I can steal
you back from her!
[JUNICHI]
Huh?!
This is like something
out of an old cartoon!
That's all, folks!
[AYUMI]
Ayumi, checking in!
[KOKORO]
Kokoro, too!
[NENE]
Nene, three!
[AYUMI]
Nene, get out of here!
[KOKORO] We don't need
anyone else bugging us.
[NENE] What? I don't
understand why you're mad.
[AYUMI, KOKORO]
Well, we don't understand you,
tits on toothpicks!
[NENE] You talk a lot for
girls with small boobs.
[KOKORO, AYUMI scream]
[KOKORO] You guys, the
preview's almost done!
[AYUMI, KOKORO, NENE]
Oh, no, we didn't--