Do, re, mi, fa, so much ass
I don't know where to look!
Wow, this beach is everything
it's cracked up to be!
[KEIGO]
I still can't believe I'm here!
I get to do what
the popular kids do!
I feel like the fugly
girl in the movie
who takes off her glasses and
suddenly has value as a person!
It's a wet dream come true!
[MINORU]
It's not a dream,
it's my fantasy!
[RANKO chuckles]
[RANKO]
There you boys are.
[KEIGO, SHINPEI yell]
[SHINPEI, KEIGO chattering]
[YUI]
The beach is so lovely.
[SHINPEI] Score! We've got
ourselves a proper girl!
[KEIGO] The boobs to bikini
ratio here is on point!
Hey, Junichi!
Recognize my swimsuit?
Can you believe it's
the same one I wore
when we were little kids?
Guh. Uh, think maybe you
need a bit more coverage
than you did back then.
[giggles]
[YUKANA]
That sea breeze feels so good.
[JUNICHI] Holy Shnykees.
Yukana really is the best girl.
Can you believe it?
We're finally here!
Oh, yeah.
So let's do beach!
[OTHERS]
Hells yeah!
[NENE] One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
[KEIGO, SHINPEI]
Go roku shichi hachi .
There you go. Enjoy!
[YUI]
Aw, thanks for setting it up.
By the way, I'm feeling
a little parched now.
So could you be a doll
and fetch me--?
[NENE]
Hey, Junichi!
Let's go for a dip!
[giggles]
[YUKANA]
Uh, boyfriend!
[JUNICHI]
Uh. Yukana?
Get your fine ass in here!
[chuckles]
Hey, don't worry
about your A-cups.
They'll get bigger.
No, a cup of juice.
[NENE] Wait, I can't run that
fast on my toothpick legs!
[YUKANA laughs]
[yelps]
[YUKANA]
Aww! Sorry, I couldn't resist.
Let me return the favor!
[giggles]
[YUKANA]
Junichi! You got me all wet!
[RANKO laughs]
Ha. See? I can
make you wet, too!
[YUKANA] Oh, you are so dead,
bitch! I'll show you wet!
[yells]
Nene.
It looked like you might
be hella-drowning,
so I thought, maybe you'd
like to use my bouyancy.
[JUNICHI] Oh! Feels like two
ginormous passion fruits
massaging my back!
Come on, get off me, Nene!
That's right, I'm the squirter.
Better watch your back.
Man, this beach trip isn't
quite the nonstop poon orgy
that I hoped it would be.
Ditto. I was thinking
the same exact thing.
But still... Oh. Mh-hm-hm.
It's not all bad.
Yeah, this view doesn't suck.
I'm shitfaced!
I can still drive!
[chuckles]
[SHINPEI] This is the natural
habitat of the camel-toe,
I'd stick my thumb
in that cloaca.
[KEIGO]
Man, I sure do love the beach.
[MAN A]
Ready?
[LITTLE GIRL A]
Up high, Daddy!
[MINORU]
I've found it...
[BOTH giggling]
[MINORU]
Shangri-La!
Set!
[NENE]
There!
[RANKO]
I've got you now!
[grunts]
Ouch, that looked supes painful.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, I think I'll survive.
[RANKO laughs]
Sorry, dude. That's just my
instinct when I see balls.
Oh yeah, right. You mean your
warrior princess instinct?
Yukana, wanna go see
what the food sitch
is like around here?
Oh, for sure.
We skimped out on the hotel
and didn't get a meal plan,
so we should figure out
what to do about dinner.
All right, we're gonna
peace out. Laters!
Okay. See ya soon!
Well, I was planning to
lay out for a bit, so--
Hey! ♪ Do you wanna
build a sandcastle? ♪
You're kidding.
What are we, like, five?
Fine, it's not like I've
got anything better to do.
Yay! It's gonna be huge!
[NENE laughing]
We did it!
Yeah, if I were a sand
king, I'd live in there.
Oh, totally! Our sandcastle
is hella-dope as eff!
Uh. Yeah, it's phat!
But just think how much
"doper" it could be
if we focused on the details
a little bit more, right, fam?
You sure are anal.
About details.
[giggles]
Let's make it even doper!
[YUI] Hey, Junichi, you wanna
finger an arrowslit for me?
You know, so the archers can
shoot off a load of arrows.
Not sure what that means.
Uh. Huh?
[JUNICHI]
Who the fuck are those guys?
Hey, Junichi!
Where are you going?
[JUNICHI]
Sorry. Be right back.
Hot!
[JUNICHI]
Huh, I was coming over here
to save Yukana and Ranko, but...
...I don't have any
right to tell a girl
who she can and can't talk to.
Do I?
Oh, hey, boyfriend!
Well, y'all are awesome,
but our friend's here,
so we gotta say bye!
Thanks for saving us, Junichi.
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
[gasps]
[JUNICHI] I'm so in there! If
boobs were bread I'm balogna!
[RANKO] Those cheese dick
asshats were shady A-F.
I mean, just 'cause we're
wearing teeny bikinis,
that's not an invite to creep.
So you did good, Mister Virgin.
[JUNICHI]
Oh. Well, glad I could help.
Thanks, guys,
for keepin' watch.
Oh, yeah, no problemo!
Yeah, we'll watch
your junk anytime!
[RANKO] Anyway, boys,
we're here now, so you can go.
Must be exhausting keeping
your eyes glued to our junk
without actually being
able to do anything.
So go take care
of yourselves now.
You boys've earned it!
Oh. Alrighty then.
Yeah. Guess we'll
be going, Minoru.
[YUKANA]
So, Junichi.
Can you squirt some on my back?
[JUNICHI] Great Googly Moogly,
I get to touch her!
[RANKO] Yeah, and while
you're at it, Mister Virgin,
do me, too, 'kay.
Free-range boobs!
I didn't know girls actually
did that in real life!
Don't be shy. Tan lines suck.
[grunts]
[YUKANA] Uh, Junichi.
I hope you don't mind.
[JUNICHI]
Shangri-La!
C'mon, junichi get the lead out.
Yeah, let's hurry it up!
[JUNICHI]
Oh no, what am I gonna do?
I'm not equipped
to deal with this!
What are we gonna do?
[CONSCIENCE] Who knew
we'd be asked to perform
such a nasty task?
Oh, if only he were here.
[JUNICHI] Alas,
I destroyed that degenerate
with my own handsome hands.
Ho! It's a miracle!
[LIBIDO]
Boners!
[JUNICHI]
Let's get ready to rub girls!
Mister Virgin, wow!
Uh, the way you're touching us,
it's, uh, getting kinda pervy.
[JUNICHI]
Uh?
Don't you fucking listen to her!
Do it harder!
Give it to me harder!
Hey, you're talking all
sexy on purpose, aren't you?
Man, we've spent the whole day
dragging this beached pedofile.
[SHINPEI] Mm. Barely noon
it is, young Padawan.
Only half gone the day is.
[KEIGO]
What do you mean?
Answer me!
[SHINPEI] Remember, we're
staying here overnight,
and the night time
isa the right time.
Wait a second, are you sayin--?
[SHINPEI] Yes, but in
order to pull it off,
we're going to have to get
Kissass on board.
Here. I made this
one just for you.
[NENE]
Oh, that's okay,
I already fixed a
kebab for Junichi,
and this one has all of
his favorites on it, see?
[SHINPEI]
Yo, Junichi!
What are you dorks doing
all the way over here?
Nice of you to finally
join us. Let's chat.
Huh? What is it?
You're makin' me nervous.
'Kay, listen up.
We've gotta bring you up to
speed on our genius plan.
[JUNICHI]
Uhh...
[YUKANA]
Those kebabs were delish.
Yeah, inn food's okay,
but sometimes it's nice
to try something
outside the bento box.
Are you hos ready to go?
[NENE]
Ready, Freddy.
[YUKANA]
Then let's skedaddle.
[chuckles]
All right, men,
it's Zero Dark Dirty!
[SHINPEI]
Here.
Come on, guys, you can't
go through with this!
It's wrong!
No, what's wrong, maggot,
is you've got a fricking bun
where your hot dog should be.
[JUNICHI] For real, though,
peeping is a serious crime!
Not to mention a gross
invasion of privacy!
[SHINPEI] Junichi,
you poor, naïve bastard.
You don't know the first thing
about women, do you?
Allow me to red-pill you, bro.
If you don't try to sneak
a peek at a chick,
you're basically calling
her a ass face swamp-beast!
So it's rude not to
peep at their pipis.
That's insane!
Wow, what a douche.
Why do you wanna give those
girls body image issues?
How am I the bad guy here?
[SHINPEI]
Never mind that!
You've got a choice
to make here!
If you don't join us and peep,
you're a maggot, son!
You'll be disrespecting those
girls, and yourself, Gomer!
C'mon, dude, don't you
wanna catch a glimpse
of Yukana's yabbos?
Of course I freakin' do!
I wanna see 'em more
than you guys do!
I wanna see 'em more than
anything in the world!
Whoa, chill out, dude,
they're just yabbos.
It's because I wanna see
'em so much that I can't.
Calm down, Junichi, you're
not making any sense.
[JUNICHI]
I wanna see 'em.
I just don't really
wanna ogle them
through night vision goggles.
You don't like gazongas,
fine, stay here.
But don't get in the way
of our nocturnal mission.
I'm going!
[SHINPEI] All right!
Now you're a real man!
Hey, you in, Minoru?
[MINORU] Nah, I'm going
to the men's bath.
[SHINPEI]
Better than diddlin' kiddies.
[MINORU] See, they let fathers
bring their little girls
into the men's bath as long
as they're not too old.
And "not-too-old" is
my target demographic.
[YUKANA sighs]
Feels so good.
[RANKO]
We've got a bomb-ass view, too.
How can you just stand there?
Aren't you worried
someone might see you?
[NENE gasps]
Like a peeper?
It's fine, it's fine.
Security around the
women's bath here
is tighter than your
virgin vajayjay, 'kay?
[RANKO]
The one-eyed Willie innkeeper
said it'd be impossible
for anyone to peep on us.
[YUI] Well, in that case,
I guess it should be safe.
Wow. It really is lovely.
[NENE] It so beautiful, it
reminds me of an album cover.
What a marvelous view.
[MANAMI'S DAD]
No running, sweetie!
[MANAMI] Look, Daddy!
Look at me! I'm a seagull!
[MINORU]
Heaven does exist.
And it's right here.
[YUKANA grunts]
--I'm in heaven. Hooter heaven.
--What are you--? No.
'Kay, thanks, I think my
nips are all clean now.
Oh, you know
you love it, baby!
I find this problematic.
You know, Nene's boobs are,
like, way bigger than mine.
[RANKO growls]
[yelps]
Now, now, Nene.
Doctor Ranko just wants to
give you a little mamogram.
[NENE] Um, I'm not sure
you're a licensed physician.
[RANKO] Oh, God, these
are the bomb-dot-com!
Yukana, you have
got to feel these!
Uh, do you mind if I give
'em a little squeeze?
What? Of course I mind!
[YUKANA]
Whoa, these honkers are bonkers!
[RANKO]
I know, right?
[NENE]
Help! Somebody save me!
Hey, these jubblies are
bigger than they look.
[screams]
[YUKANA laughs]
Hey, what's so funny?
It's just, this is fun.
Yeah, what's so fun about it?
Well, all's I was sayin'
was, I'm happy you came!
[YUI]
Let's see how you like it!
[YUKANA, RANKO laughing]
[NENE whines]
[SHINPEI humming]
[SHINPEI]
Halt!
It's a booby trap.
The innkeeper put 'em out here
to keep us from the boobies.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, I can use this!
[beeping]
Oopsie-doopsie. I seem to
have by accident set it off.
Now, let us run away.
For surely the innkeeper
will be here soon.
[SHINPEI] No. There'll
be no need for that.
You see, I planted that
device ahead of time.
It's a fake.
C'mon, man, use your noggin.
You really think an innkeeper
would set up traps
just to keep pervs like us
from getting close
to the women's bath?
That kinda thing only
happens in anime.
Whoa, you guys tricked me?
Ha! Says the lowlife
backstabbing traitor!
Since you've done this
kinda thing before,
we knew we needed to test you!
What? Done this before?
I don't remember that episode!
And anyway, I haven't
done anything wrong!
Yeah? Well, let's
put that to a vote.
Those who think Junichi Hashiba
is innocent of treason...
Aye!
All those who
know he's guilty...
[BOTH]
Aye!
Screw the popular vote!
Oh, get over it!
You lost fair and square!
Get back here, traitor!
[JUNICHI] Damn it! I've gotta
get outta these woods somehow!
[screams]
Is he dead?
'Course not, he's
the main character.
And we still have
two episodes to go.
Come on, move out!
Sneak, sneak, sneak.
[KEIGO]
Look! The women's bath is close!
It'll be an
all-you-can-peep muff-et!
A total whore-gasbord!
An ass-eteria--
[screams]
Keigo!
[KEIGO grunting]
[KEIGO]
Pull me up!
What the--? C'mon, dude!
[KEIGO] I thought you said
there was no way an innkeeper
would set up traps like this!
[SHINPEI] I don't know,
it seemed ridiculous, but--
[KEIGO]
Shinpei!
This is FUBAR.
TARFUN FISHMO bro!
No! We can't just cut and run!
We've lost too much already
in service of this mission!
Our best friend
is dead. To us now!
Don't let his
sacrifice be in vain!
[KEIGO]
But, Shinpei.
Do you remember when
you chose the route
that was sure to make the
heroine hate you, Keigo,
knowing full well it would
deprive you of a happy ending,
all so you could finally
get to the damn treasure?
Where's those balls?
In my pants!
[SHINPEI]
Look!
Right in front of us, soldier,
is a route that we haven't
been able to complete yet.
And if we give up now,
we may never again
have an opportunity
to complete this one!
I see now.
In order to seek out my life's
treasure, I'm gonna have to--
[KEIGO,SHINPEI yelling]
[BOTH]
Down!
[BOTH screaming]
[KEIGO, SHINPEI]
Up!
[laughing]
Hell yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' about!
We're invincible! Nothing can--
[KEIGO]
Shinpei, what's wrong?
Sh-Shinpei!
They got me. I've been--
[thud]
Uh! Shinpei!
Gasp.
I'm not gonna make it.
It's all goin' black now.
Hang on! They're
just suction cups!
You don't have to lie
just to comfort me.
Now go on, leave me behind,
and just go, y'hear me?
Complete the mission and
go live out our dream.
Hang in there!
You know I-I can't complete
the mission without you!
There's no way to copy
my save data to you!
Keigo, earn this!
[wails]
[KEIGO]
Game over, man! Game over!
Ooh, fireworks!
[RANKO]
Okay, now that is straight fire!
Pretty, innit it?
[GIRLS laughing]
[YUI]
Are you sure these are safe?
Oh, you're coming to.
Huh?
[JUNICHI yelps]
[JUNICHI]
Yukana?
Hey, sleepyhead.
We just came down here to
light up some sparklers,
and then found you
passed out on the beach.
[JUNICHI] Oh, right. I fell
off that cliff because--
Where are Shinpei and Keigo?
Mean your annoying
pervy friends?
Well, I guess...
I don't really know
what happened,
but they were found out cold
in the forest behind the inn.
[JUNICHI]
Huh, you don't say.
[YUKANA] And apparently,
your husky friend
suffered an extreme
loss of fluids,
and passed out in the bath.
You guys cause so much drama!
Uh, sorry.
It's cool.
But you guys might wanna
leave an extra-generous tip
for the inn staff when we leave.
[YUKANA] Y'know, this has really
been a super fun trip, Junichi.
Turned out a little different
from how I imagined it.
But then maybe that's
for the best, right?
[YUKANA giggles]
Sorry. I ruined it.
Say what? I just told
you I had a great time.
Let's come back, just us two!
So what's your idea
of the perfect date
if you could do
anything in the world?
Uh. In the world?
[JUNICHI] Guess I should
try to think of something
that would make Yukana happy.
[JUNICHI] Uh, how about going to
an amusement park? At night?
[YUKANA]
Aww, that's cute.
And kinda romantic.
[JUNICHI]
Really?
[YUKANA] Well, you tried to
think of something good,
and that's what counts.
[JUNICHI] Well, you know it's
'cause I care about you.
[YUKANA]
That's so sweet.
Alrighty then, let's go to one.
An amusement park. At night.
That was really fun.
Oh, yeah.
I was wondering.
[YUKANA]
Hm?
[DAI]
Whoa, Yukana?
[YUKANA]
Dai, is that you?
Who's he?
[AYUMI]
Yo, Ayumi here!
[KOKORO]
And Kokoro!
[GUYS] Why do the three of us
have to talk at the same time?
[AYUMI] Just be grateful
you're even here at all!
[KOKORO] If you each got to
talk, we'd have fewer lines!
[AYUMI]
Y'know, in the manga,
you guys didn't
have names, either!
[SHINPEI] So why do you get to
be such a big part of the show?
[GUYS]
Aw, you're making me blush.
[AYUMI]
Shut up!