[JUNICHI]
Man, I still can't believe it.
She actually agreed
to go out with me.
So, yeah. We can
go out. Boyfriend.
[grumbles]
[JUNICHI] But none of
this makes any sense.
Why would a smokin' hot, popular
gal with big boobs like her
go out with a guy like me?
I mean, just from a
logical perspective!
Bet she just wanted to
make me lower my guard
so she could tell the school
I'm a pathetic, gullible loser.
So jaded!
You can't just go through life
doubting everyone's intentions!
What good's it do to
question Yukana's motives?
We're supposed to be dating her
now, in case you've forgotten!
Hah. Oh, you sweet,
innocent baby.
Listen, okay. Gals
are terrifying entities.
Fundamentally,
they're just not like us.
They're a completely
different species.
Really?
That's precisely the sort
of provincial thinking
that's keeping us a virgin!
[BAD growls]
Your stupid face is what's
keeping us a virgin!
[CONSCIENCE]
Hey, violence isn't the answer!
No hitting! No hitting!
[LIBIDO]
Whoosh. Twinkle!
Swoosh, swoosh, swoosh!
Pop-pop! Mask on!
Pow! Pow! Pow! Bam!
Ba-Ba-Ba-Boner!
Enough of your useless
bickering already!
The only thing that
matters is getting close
to that banging
gal's banging bod!
[YUKANA giggles]
[YUKANA]
It's kinda funny, isn't it?
How just a second ago, we
were so focused on class,
and now look at us.
But we can't do this in here.
We could get into
so much trouble!
[YUKANA] Aww, but getting
into trouble's fun.
You don't wanna be a
naughty boy with me?
Naughty? Whaddaya
mean by "naughty"?
Oh, how 'bout I just show you?
[yelps]
You can decide if you
think it's naughty after.
[JUNICHI]
Yeah, let's do that.
[groans]
[JUNICHI]
Ouch.
[JUNICHI] Last night I
enjoyed, or pre-enjoyed,
my little wet dream, but now
I have to worry about reality.
Y'know, to be honest,
it doesn't even feel like
I'm actually dating
Yukana in real life.
I mean, when I asked
her out yesterday,
she sure seemed to be
having fun toying with me.
[YUKANA] Come on, you know
you wanna see 'em, right?
[JUNICHI] Maybe I'm better
off just avoiding her
from here on out.
[SHINPEI]
Yo.
[JUNICHI yells]
'Sup?
Oh, it's just you guys.
So, uh, yeah, man, we're, um,
sorry 'bout yesterday, dude.
We, uh, went a little overboard.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, yeah, almost forgot.
These a-holes were the ones
who forced me to ask her
out in the first place!
Anyway, what's past
is past right?
How'd it go with her?
I'm sure she was awful.
Did she knee you in
the giggle-berries?
Tell ol' Shinny everything.
[JUNICHI growls]
It was bad.
I'm pretty sure Yukana
put me on her hit list.
She's gonna make it her mission
to ruin the rest of
my high school life,
and maybe beyond that!
Uh, for real?
Did not expect that.
[JUNICHI] You guys, I-I
don't know what the hell
I'm gonna do here.
[SHINPEI]
Hey, don't sweat it.
[JUNICHI]
Huh?
No matter what
humiliating rumors
that chick spreads about you.
No matter how many whedgies
and purple nurples you receive.
No matter what happens,
we'll be there for you, bro!
Because we will...
[ALL]
...always be your loyal friends!
Wow, you guys.
[JUNICHI]
That's right.
They'll always be here for me.
There's no need to feel down.
What's the old saying?
"Pals before gals"?
Sorry, just got a text.
[JUNICHI]
What?!
[GUYS]
She sent a sexy selfie?
[JUNICHI]
Oh, right! Yesterday, she--
Hey, lemme see your phone.
[JUNICHI]
Uh, sure.
There. Now you've got
my phone number, okay?
Ha-ha. Man, this sucks.
She made me trade contact
info for emergencies.
[JUNICHI laughs]
[JUNICHI]
Ouch.
Uh, yeah, who are you?
You've got the popular cooties,
so talk to the hand.
Any man as lucky as you
is no friend of mine!
I hate you so much!
I'm losing my mind because of
how effed up this situation is!
So's Yukana have
a little sister?
I'm not too particular,
but if she still wets the bed,
that's kind of the
sweet spot for me.
Hey, guys, wait,
what happened to us always
being loyal friends?
I thought "always" lasted
longer than that.
[SHINPEI]
You traitor.
[KEIGO] Why'd we ever
give a damn about him?
Just hang on a second, will ya?
It's not what it looks
like, okay? I promise!
All right, then riddle me this.
Did you two lovebirds
swap your spit yet?
Wha--? Really?
Of course not!
It hasn't even been a day!
[SHINPEI grunts]
Now, listen up, and understand.
To a gal, a kiss is
just like saying "hi."
And if she's actually in to a
guy, then whoa buddy, look out,
'cause she'll smooch
on that lucky bastard
as often as she takes a breath!
Seriously?
Where do you even
get this stuff from?
Does that go for the
preteen set, too?
[JUNICHI]
Well, Yukana certainly is a gal.
And she doesn't seem
stingy with affection.
On the off chance
she was serious
about wanting to date me...
Did you sleep so good, baby?
Uh, ya, I sure did.
[YUKANA]
Time for your good-morning kiss.
[JUNICHI]
So you mean she and I
are gonna be
Frenching like crazy?
That's right!
Looks like you're finally
starting to get it, Junichi.
But there's a proper
order to things,
and you need to set
the stage correctly
if you wanna loosen
those sweet tangerine lips.
Teach me, my sensei!
[chuckles]
[SHINPEI]
Teach you, I shall. Mm.
Your first lesson:
Invite her to karaoke!
Really, dude?
Karaoke's so lame.
[KEIGO, MINORU]
Uh-huh.
You naïve virgins!
This is exactly
why you three are,
and will always be, virgins!
[ALL]
What about you?
[SHINPEI]
Listen up, pump chumps!
See, the popular kids all use
karaoke as a discreet way
to "get a room."
You're kidding.
Oh, my intel is rock solid.
I learned it firsthand
while scrubbin' booths
at a karaoke joint.
There I discovered a
foolproof natural law,
one which'll likely win me
the Nobel Prize someday.
I call it...
[SHINPEI]
...the Karaoke Triple-X Rule!
Wait, really?
That's the best you could do?
That name is terrible.
[SHINPEI]
No, it's not.
[ALL gasp]
[SHINPEI]
Pick pervy songs to sing,
have fun singing
a duet together,
and the girl takes
off her clothes.
When these three
elements come together,
the couple will,
without a doubt...
Spit it out, man.
...they will do the deed.
Whoa, are you serious?
[SHINPEI retches]
You okay?
Karaoke is just supposed
to be good, clean fun,
not a pretense for teens
to grope each other
like cantaloupes.
That's not what it's for.
Hey! Get it together, brother.
Don't let me die in
vain, Junichi- san.
Don't you go dying on me!
Now you invite that
girl to karaoke.
If you do, then you'll be
able to kiss her and...
...and lose your
virginity, young man.
Come on, Shinpei.
Shinpei!
[SHINPEI]
Angel boobs!
Oh, right. Karaoke, huh?
Well, now the question is,
how am I gonna ask her?
[YUI]
Good morning, Junichi.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, Yui.
Hey, what's wrong?
You look more lost in
thought than usual today.
Got something on your mind?
No, no, no, no.
It's absolutely nothing.
Nope, nothing at all.
Not a thing.
Hm. Are you sure?
I don't mind helping out.
[JUNICHI] Thanks,
but really, it's nothing.
I appreciate the offer, though.
Thank you for your concern.
[chuckling]
[JUNICHI] I mean, I can't
very well just ask Yui,
"Hey, what's the best way
to get a gal to do
karaoke with me
so I can do the nasty with her?"
[YUKANA]
Good morning, Junichi!
Morning wood!
I mean, good morning!
[JUNICHI]
They're so soft.
Did you get the selfie
I sent this morning?
Pretty cute, wasn't it?
Yeah, pretty cute.
That's the word I would
use to describe it, cutie.
I know, right? Hashtag no
filter. Hashtag seriously!
Oh, really? Wow,
that's awesome.
[YUKANA]
Isn't it?
Huh, that's odd. Were Yukana
and Junichi always this close?
Oh, right. Heads up, everyone.
The two of us started
dating yesterday.
[STUDENTS]
What?!
[sighs]
[JUNICHI]
This morning was a mess.
Kids who've never given me the
time of day were all over me.
I haven't had the chance to ask
Yukana to go do karaoke, yet.
And ever since this morning,
Yukana's been busy fielding
questions from her friends.
I can't even say
two words to her.
Oh, stop. You girls
are terrible.
Hey! Wait, I'm heading
home, too, guys.
Wait! Hang on! Did ya hear me?
[JUNICHI]
What's up with you guys?
You coulda at least waited
for me to catch up.
[ALL]
Uhh?
Dude, you're dating one
of the hottest chicks
in the entire school.
No reason to hang out with
us virgins anymore, right?
I hope the school burns down
and you die in the fire.
After we've left, of course!
So did you ask Yukana if
she's got a little sister
for me yet, dumb nuts?
Heh. Why the cold shoulder?
Honestly, I'm more surprised
about this than
anyone, but still--
Oh, shut up!
I don't give a hoot!
I'm jealous and I want
you to burn alive!
Oh, now don't say that.
Anyway, you guys made me
ask her out, remember?
I won't listen to
reason! Butt munch!
[JUNICHI]
But I wanna live.
Why do they have
to be so selfish?
[YUKANA]
Oh, Junichi!
Oh, hey there.
[JUNICHI yelps]
I'm guessing you're free
after school, right?
Spend time with me.
[NENE]
♪ Let's go, let's go home. ♪
[JUNICHI]
Hold it a second, will ya?
[YUKANA] Oh, quit dragging
your heels and come with me.
[JUNICHI]
But I--
Junichi, where are you going?
Nene? What's up?
Um, why are you two
holding hands like that?
Uh, no duh, we're boyfriend
and girlfriend now,
so of course we're
holding hands.
You're kidding me, Junichi!
You big, dumb oaf!
Oh, so is that girl
your little sister?
She's so cute and
pocket-sized, huh?
[JUNICHI chuckles]
Guess she's kinda
like a little sister.
Ah.
Well, anyway, we should
get going now, 'kay?
Hey, wait, I never
got a chance to ask,
but where are we going?
Just somewhere nice and private.
We can be as loud as we want.
And feel oh so good.
You don't mean-- Holy cow!
[YUKANA]
Two, please.
[KARAOKE CLERK A]
For how long?
[YUKANA] Hmm, let's say an
hour to start off, I guess?
[JUNICHI]
Karaoke?
I thought she was talking about
going to get a room somewh--
Wait a second.
[SHINPEI] It's a discreet
way to "get a room."
[JUNICHI]
Well, that worked out.
Oh no, I just realized!
I've only ever done karaoke
with those three
idiot friends of mine!
What the hell kinda song
am I s'posed to sing
with a gal like her?
I'm so glad you were
around, Junichi.
For some reason, I was just
dying to sing karaoke today,
but none of my friends
were up for it.
Ah, so that's what happened.
I really wanted to belt out
some tunes with my squad,
but whatever.
[JUNICHI chuckles]
[JUNICHI] So I'm just
the backup plan, huh?
[YUKANA] But there's nothing
I can do about that,
so here we are,
having our first date
dressed in our school uniforms.
[giggles]
Oh, wow, she's so cute.
[JUNICHI]
So this is a date, huh?
In that case, I really don't
know what to sing now.
[chuckles nervously]
[JUNICHI] "Please do not
use this room for--"
Whoa, whoa, whoa, seriously?
Can't believe four-eyes
was telling the truth!
[STUDENTS laughing]
They wouldn't put up
a sign like that...
...unless some kids
had a kara-orgy here.
Hey, I'm back.
Orgy!
Do you like have something
caught in your throat?
No, I, um--
Well, I bought us some juice.
Oh, thanks. Here.
[JUNICHI] I'm sure Yukana
wouldn't skip kissing
and go straight to
hard-core humping.
[YUKANA] 'Scuse me, just
gotta squeeze through here.
[YUKANA] There we go. It sure
is tight in here, isn't it?
Okay, I'll do the first song.
[JUNICHI]
What the hell was that just now?
Did she do that on purpose?
Was she trying to motorboat me?
Or make me motorboat her?
Who does the motorboating?
All I know is, if she sits
on my lap right now,
it's not going to be a
very comfy seat for her.
I'm as hard as a set of keys.
[YUKANA]
Ah, there we go.
Uh, hey, Yukana,
what are you doing?
[YUKANA chuckles]
[YUKANA] Rub-a-dub-dub,
who's got a chub?
[yelping]
Oh, my.
Gee whiz, Junichi,
you're so stiff.
We can't, not here.
Read the sign.
Relax or you won't
be able to sing.
Come now, loosen up.
Oh, there's no way
I can stand up there
and sing in this condition.
[YUKANA]
In that case...
[JUNICHI gasps]
[YUKANA] This oughta help you
relax. I give great massages.
Mic check, mic check.
One, two, three.
[JUNICHI] Ah! My mic's about
to give her some feedback!
[YUKANA] ♪ It falls
like tears from above ♪
[JUNICHI] Huh. Guess
I'm overthinking this.
I mean, look at her.
She's having a great time.
All she wanted was
to sing some karaoke.
[YUKANA] ♪ It's so simple.
Simple as can be. ♪
♪ And you and me ♪
♪ we can paint a rainbow
across the cloudy sky. ♪
♪ We control the weather,
don't you forget. ♪
♪ And we won't let
the summer end ♪
♪ because we're not ready yet. ♪
Hey, wait. You didn't
put anything in yet?
Oh, I'm still trying to decide.
Why don't you just go
ahead and sing again?
You sure? Ooh, that's my jam!
[JUNICHI]
Man, this is bad.
I need to sing something. Uh.
But I don't know any songs
from the top picks list.
The only songs I can sing
are all from anime,
and that's gotta be a major
turnoff for a gal like her.
Hmm.
I'll just have to
find an anime song
that doesn't sound like
it's from an anime.
[YUKANA]
♪ I know what you want. ♪
♪ I want it, too. ♪
♪ I can't wait to take
you inside, my love. ♪
♪ Hold up now, it's not
like just anyone will do. ♪
♪ But inside of me, ♪
♪ the memories of my past
mistakes scream loudly. ♪
♪ I want you to split me open. ♪
♪ So wide I almost rip in two. ♪
♪ Without you by my side,
I feel empty. ♪
♪ Like a hole without a screw. ♪
[JUNICHI]
Whoa, this is--
Calm down, Junichi! I'm sure
it's just a coincidence!
Probably.
[YUKANA sighs]
Why am I the only
one singing here?
Come on, Junichi,
show me what you can do.
I just know so many hit songs,
it's hard to narrow it down!
[YUKANA]
Here.
How 'bout a classic song
everyone knows by heart?
[music plays]
Hey, this is from... an anime.
Here.
Do you mind if we
sing it together?
Um, sure.
[YUKANA, JUNICHI]
♪ Heart watcher. ♪
♪ Been watching me,
been right there by my side. ♪
♪ You're with me like a
nurse is with a doctor. ♪
♪ Each day and every night. ♪
♪ And no matter what,
we won't be apart. ♪
♪ That's because you
saved my heart. ♪
Wow, that song really
brings back some memories.
For sure, but I'm
kinda surprised
that you would know
an anime song.
Really, that surprises you?
There's not a kid alive
from our generation
who wouldn't know that one.
'Sides, I know plenty of
other anime songs, too,
so queue 'em up all you want.
[JUNICHI]
Whoa.
Did she know I was nervous,
and try to make me feel better?
Hey, let's do another
one together, okay?
Ooh, I bet you've heard
this one before!
Uh, lemme take a look.
[gasps]
[JUNICHI]
Hang on, this is a--
[GUYS]
Score! Do it! Do it!
[JUNICHI]
No, no, no, no, no!
Yukana would never operate
according to such an obscene,
and, frankly, stupid rule.
It's getting warm
in here, huh?
There.
[JUNICHI]
Oh, come on!
Oh, wow, look at that.
All of the signs
have been lit up.
[LIBIDO]
Woo-hoo-hoo!
That means they have to
start ba-ba-ba-boinking now!
All right, everybody,
just cool your jets, okay?
That dumb four-eyed kid just
pulled this stuff outta his ass.
[LIBIDO]
Bang!
Good point. And besides, we
should wait and make it special.
[ALL]
Hm?
Oh, good grief.
This is why you gentlemen
are still virgins.
Do you honestly want to
embarrass the young lady?
[ALL]
Holy crap, that's cool me!
You're so cool!
See, the nubile Yukana
has begun to blossom,
giving root to a most precious
red rose by the name of desire.
What sort of men are you if
you don't answer her call?
For one cannot be a man if
you only worry about oneself.
Sometimes, in order
to be a real man,
you must sacrifice your own
desires for those of a woman.
Catch my drift?
It's not like any of us are
dying to be "real men," anyway.
And even if we were somehow
to become "real men,"
there's no guarantee that we'd
lose our virginity then, either.
Yeah, that's right.
And if Yukana didn't really have
those intentions after all...
[BAD, CONSCIENCE sigh]
[LIBIDO]
In that case,
I guess I'll just
have to unsheathe
the eternal saber of courtship
and take her myself!
Woo! Woo!
[COOL chuckles]
[COOL] I'm not here to denounce
embracing one's own libido.
However, before
you dip your wick,
there is something that you
must first do for the lady.
[BOTH]
Oh, really, what's that?
[JUNICHI]
Why,
give her a passionate kiss
on the lips, of course.
Those who fail to do so are
not men, but rather, scum.
And I do not wish for us
to be scum. Do you?
[COOL]
Kiss. Nibble. Slip the tongue.
[JUNICHI]
I'm so sorry, Yukana.
That's the real reason
why you wanted
to go karaoke-ing
with me, isn't it?
Fine.
[gasps]
[JUNICHI] If I can't do this,
then I'm not a real man!
Hey.
You've got a nose
hair sticking out.
[JUNICHI]
Uh, what now?
[COOL screams]
[ALL]
Cool me!
'Scuse me. I'll be right back.
[YUKANA]
Dummy.
You were totally trying
to kiss me, weren't you?
I'm not like that. I can't just
kiss someone so easily.
[JUNICHI]
It's over.
For the rest of my life,
every time I even think
about making a move,
all that I'll hear is, "You've
got a nose hair sticking out"!
Curse you, nose hair!
You pointless, tickly bastard!
Oh, Yukana, please
forgive my nose
and every last snot-encrusted
hair inside it!
[YUKANA]
Hey, I had fun today.
Next time, you might
even be my first choice
for a karaoke partner.
[laughs]
Yeah, me, too!
[YUKANA]
All right, now let's go.
Come on, get up.
The ground's filthy.
[JUNICHI]
Yeah. Okay!
Hey, Yukana, wait for me!
[YUKANA]
Well, hurry up!
[JUNICHI] Aww, I think
my nostril's bleeding.
[RANKO]
Rude.
[AYUMI]
Yo, Ayumi here!
[KOKORO]
And Kokoro!
[AYUMI] Kokoro had some trivia
last time, so now it's my turn!
[KOKORO]
Let's hear it!
[AYUMI] Do you know why
they call it "karaoke"?
[KOKORO]
It's from the Japanese word
for "empty" and
"orchestra," right?
So hey, what's your fun trivia?
[AYUMI] You did that on
purpose, didn't you?
[KOKORO] No, seriously,
what's your trivia?