[YUI] The world totally
revolves around me.
[STUDENT A]
Wow, Yui!
You're, like, really
smart, you know that?
Like, inventor of the
fidget spinner smart!
You're too kind.
[STUDENT B] And you're so cute,
you could stop traffic,
causing a disemboweling
three-car pileup!
You're very sweet.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[JUNICHI]
'Scuse me, Yui?
Did you drop this?
Huh? Oh, ya.
Uh, thanks.
Good doggy.
[JUNICHI barks]
[JUNICHI]
Hey, guys. Junichi Hashiba here.
You've caught me in the middle
of my ongoing
research into "gals."
Ugh, this old fart on the
train today asked me
if I would move my bag
so he could sit down.
Ugh, I'm glad he had a stroke!
[JUNICHI]
See, for a variety of reasons,
I've been interacting with
a lot of "gals" lately.
For real, though, you can't
just leave a person on "read."
That kinda thing should
be illegal, am I right?
So I'm just clicking
around the interwebs,
looking to see what kind of
gals are out there in the world,
you know, aside from
just Yukana and Ranko.
Like Jane Goodall with the apes.
Huh? You wanna know my bra size?
Thirty-six double-deez nuts,
that's my bra size, fool!
[JUNICHI] This is purely
for education purposes,
so I can better understand
Yukana and Ranko.
I can't go further than this.
I'll get in trouble. And
then I'll need a spanking.
[JUNICHI]
I'm doing this all for Yukana!
It's not like I wanna be looking
at boobs on the Internet!
Hi, welcome to Bwaht Channel.
Hey there, how's
everybody doing tonight?
Your favorite mistress
is doing dandy.
Now, most of my servants
are doing a pretty good job.
But there's this one individual
who's getting a
bit too arrogant.
I think I may even have to
punish this little troublemaker.
What do you guys think of that?
[BOA]
Oh, you guys think so, too, huh?
I figured you might.
[JUNICHI]
You're cute.
[STUDENT DD]
Good morning, Yui.
[YUI]
Good morning.
[STUDENT EE]
Good morning, Yui.
[YUI]
Good morning.
Oh, hey. Good morning, Yui.
[YUI]
Thanks for greeting me so warmly
each and every day,
my humble maid.
You're cleaning quite
well today, Sebastian.
Keep it up now.
Ooh, thanks for taking care
of the flowers for me.
My servants are doing a bang-up
job today. They really are.
[JUNICHI]
Morning.
--[KEIGO] Yo.
--[MINORU] 'Sup?
So what are you guys
talking about here?
Well, Keigo's been
goin' on and on.
He won't shut up about this
cute webcam girl he saw online
while he was jerkin'
it last night.
No, she was super cute!
Hold on a sec.
I'll show her to you.
[MINORU] Uh, hey, so how
old do you think she was?
Like, was she wearing
footie pajamas...
[KEIDO] You're creeping out
our fans! Ah, here it is!
Lemme see.
All right, see ya guys later.
Thanks for poppin' in on me.
Now come again soon, y'hear?
[BOTH yell]
[KEIGO] See? What'd I tell you?
She's super cute, right?
[SHINPEI]
Cute? She's spectacular!
[KEIGO]
She's a smoke show!
[JUNICHI] Hey, wait. Isn't that
the girl I saw yesterday?
She is cute, but I mean...
[SHINPEI] You could even
call her... an angel!
Or better yet, Venus!
All the allure of a gal,
but with a certain
hidden elegance, too!
She's got me thinkin': Poon!
Yeah, she's cute.
[JUNICHI]
You guys are way too excited.
Of course we're
freakin' excited!
The heavens have
bestowed upon us--
[yelps]
[KEIGO]
What is it? What's wrong?
[SHINPEI]
Not really sure exactly,
but I've got this feeling like
maybe I've met that
girl somewhere.
[KEIGO]
Huh? Seriously?
[JUNICHI] You don't,
like, know her, do you?
[KEIGO]
Oh, come on!
There's no way he'd ever
know a girl as hot as this,
let alone forget her!
[YOUNG GIRL A]
I love you, doggy.
Where do I know her from?
Damn it! This is so frustrating!
Nothing's coming to me!
I was almost there.
[KEIGO]
You can do it!
Come on, you've got this!
Just get it out!
[SHINPEI]
Damn it, I'm so close.
So freakin' close,
I can feel it.
[YUKANA]
Mmm, so yummy!
[YUKANA sighs]
[YUKANA]
Don't you just love to eat out
in the fresh air sometimes?
Uh, yeah, it's nice and airy.
[JUNICHI]
This is bad!
I'm sweating like a
horse in a glue factory!
I can't believe I'm eating
lunch with Yukana!
Wait! Could this be...?
[YUKANA]
There we go.
Say "ah!"
[JUNICHI]
Uh, ah.
You like? Taste good?
Uh, I'm so embarrassed,
I don't really know how I feel.
[YUKANA giggles]
Oh, silly boy.
Guess I'll have to do something
to make it more
appealing for you.
All right, now open wide.
I'll feed it to you.
Uh. Feed it to me?!
[JUNICHI]
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no!
Yukana's gonna--
But a man should never
turn a woman down!
Well, here I go!
[JUNICHI]
I've got this.
You okay? You look
kinda intense.
[JUNICHI yelps]
No, I'm fine! No boners here!
[JUNICHI]
Get it together, Junichi!
Nothing's gonna happen
here all because
Ranko showed up with
the Charlie Bravo.
Hey, you weren't
thinking of trying
any funny business here,
were you, Mister Virgin?
Ew, you should never do
that while you're eating.
It's way too messy!
[YUKANA, RANKO laugh]
[JUNICHI]
Actually, considering that thing
the other day with Ranko,
I bet she's still
plotting something.
Ah! She's definitely
Terrifying.
[YUI]
Um, pardon me.
I'm sorry to bother you
during lunch, but--
[JUNICHI]
Oh, hey, Yui. What's up?
[YUI] I just need to borrow
you for a second, Junichi.
Is that all right?
Wait, you need me?
Are you sure?
[grunts]
Yeah, you're right, you are
bothering us, like, hard-core.
Worst part is, you're aware
of that fact and still did it.
So, don't be sorry,
bitch, be gone!
[JUNICHI]
Uh, Ranko, why don't you--?
Now I feel bad.
I shouldn't have barged in.
It's just that I needed
to talk to Junichi.
But it's no biggie.
[JUNICHI]
Uh.
Hold on!
Talk to ya later, Junichi!
Hey, Mister Virgin.
You got something going on
with that ratchet-ass bitch?
[JUNICHI]
No, no, no!
I've got nothing to do
with her! Not a thing!
[RANKO]
Really?
'Cause that Pinocchio
nose in your pants
says you're lying to us!
I'm a teen boy!
Those just happen!
I don't buy it!
[RANKO]
She looks all innocent and pure,
but I've got a bad
feeling about that chick.
[YUKANA]
Huh?
All right, well,
I'm gonna hang out
with my friends now.
Okay. Have fun, I guess.
Aww.
You look like a sad
little puppy dog
just waiting for his master
to come back home.
No. No, I don't. Whatever.
[YUKANA chuckles]
See ya later, puppy dog!
Thanks for waiting, guys!
Ass.
[YUI]
Hey there, Junichi.
[JUNICHI screams]
Oh, Yui.
[YUI chuckles]
Sorry, but I didn't get to
talk to you at lunch time.
Oh, yeah, right. Of course.
So, um, what was it
that you needed me for?
The teacher asked me
to do him a favor
and pick up a few things
for the classroom,
but it's a lot for me to carry.
So I was hoping a big, strong
boy like you could help me out.
Uh! Wait, me?
[YUI]
Think you can handle it?
Uh, sure, if that's
all you need.
Aw, thanks. You're sweet.
[chuckles]
[CAFE MAN A] Oh, God.
Murry, we got kids in the door.
[YUI]
Thank you.
[JUNICHI]
Huh.
Weren't we supposed to be
getting school supplies?
What are we doing in
a cozy, dimly lit café?
[YUI]
Junichi.
Huh? Yeah, what now?
You want something?
What do you--?
Oh, right, uh, I guess
I'll get a coffee.
Oh, well, I'm gonna
have some tea.
Excuse me, sir!
[CAFE MAN A]
Keep your panties on...
[JUNICHI] Is Yui ignoring
a request from a teacher
and just slacking off instead?
No way. She's, like, the most
serious girl in school.
She would never.
Hmm.
Wait. I've heard about this.
[JUNICHI, SHINPEI]
There's a very specific type
of "serious" gal known as...
[SHINPEI]
...the "serious slut."
Slut. Slalalalut.
No slut-shaming now.
Now then, let's--
Uh. Yui?
What're you--? Why are
you coming over here?
It's never busy here.
This place is kind of
a hole in the wall.
Do you like holes in the wall?
Is that a question about
structural integrity?
If so then--
[JUNICHI chuckles nervously]
[JUNICHI gasps]
What are you--?
[YUI giggles]
By the way, the owner stepped
out to run some errands,
so no matter how loud
the two of us get,
nobody's gonna throw
cold water on us.
We can't do this.
I can't do this.
Not right here in
the middle of a café.
I'll just show myself out.
[JUNICHI] Why does every girl
keep doing this to--?
Hey-oh!
[JUNICHI]
Yep, could happen.
[CAFE MAN A] All right. Here's
your coffee, prince charming.
I hate my life.
So, Junichi. There's
something I wanted to ask you.
Uh. Sure. Go ahead.
Right, well, it's about Yukana.
Seems you've gotten pretty
close to her lately.
[JUNICHI]
Yeah, well, you know how it is.
Are you two, like,
dating or something?
[JUNICHI] To be honest,
I'm not really sure.
I mean, I guess, technically
we are, kinda, but...
I see. Huh. Gotta say,
that surprises me.
I really didn't expect you to
go for a girl like Yukana Yame.
For whatever reason,
I had it in my mind
that a sweet, mature,
serious girl would be
your perfect match, huh.
[JUNICHI] Yeah, I'm pretty
surprised myself, actually.
But Yukana's got a lot
of great qualities.
And the more time
I spend with her,
the more I'm learning
about who she really is.
[BOA]
Ugh, it just pisses me off!
I mean, can you
believe this crap?
Why is my servant dog
wagging his little tail
for some other rando chick?
Seriously!
And then he takes one look
at me and goes all frigid,
when he's just this
pathetic virgin!
I cannot believe this dirty
dog would dare to go out
with some raggedy-ass
girl who's not me!
And to top it all off,
the other boys in his crew
are trying to scoop
up his leftovers.
How can I just let this crap go?
My so-called "royal guard,"
this four-eyed freak,
some blonde moron, and a
total greasy pedophile.
They're not even close to loyal!
So, like, what's the point even?
Aw, I knew you guys would
totally have my back.
Thanks so much!
And I hope Mistress
Boa can continue
to count on your support!
It means the world to me!
[SHINPEI]
Print!
For real though?
[AYUMI]
Yeah, totes for real.
[BOTH laugh]
[YUKANA]
Hm? Oh. Hey, Junic--
Hey there, stud!
Where'd you come from?
So thanks for last night.
What the hell?
[AYUMI]
What's wrong, Yukacchi?
You really did.
I felt so much better
having your shoulder
to lean on, Junichi.
You're a great listener.
Huh, if you say so.
[JUNICHI chuckles]
[JUNICHI]
Glad I could be of service.
[SHINPEI]
Don't try this at home.
[KEIGO] What'd you wanna
talk to us about?
[MINORU] Yeah, why'd
you drag us back here?
Must be something pretty sketch
if you don't want
anyone else to hear.
[SHINPEI] Yeah, you bet
your sweet pippy it is.
I'll get the "free candy" van.
Castrate yourself.
Here, guys, look
what old Shinny found.
[KEIGO] That's the cam girl
from yesterday, right?
The super cute one that you
claimed to have met before.
So do you remember
where you met her?
Do you actually know that girl?
[SHINPEI]
Oh yeah, sure do.
Really? You've gotta
introduce us--
[SHINPEI]
Can't do that, dude.
[KEIGO] Come on, dude!
Don't pull a Charlie Bravo.
No, it's not like that.
See, I can't introduce you
to the girl because, well,
she's somebody that
you already know.
What?
[SHINPEI]
Here's the proof.
[KEIGO] Holy crap, it's Yui?
But she's not that kinda girl!
[SHINPEI] It's hard to tell with
all the hair and makeup,
but look closer.
[KEIGO]
No freakin' way.
It's a complete match.
[SHINPEI] And if you nut bags
had any lingering doubts...
[BOA]
My so-called "royal guard,"
this four-eyed freak,
some blonde moron,
and a total greasy pedophile.
They're not even close to loyal!
So, like, what's the point even?
Is she talking about--?
Wait, I'm the pedo?
[SHINPEI]
"Candy van," seriously?
Anyway, we can't dismiss
it. There's no doubt.
The super cute girl is...
[RANKO laughs]
[RANKO] Interesting theory
you've got there, boys.
Tell me more.
[GUYS]
Ranko Honjou?!
Let's bounce, Yukacchi.
[YUKANA]
Uh. Oh, sure.
[YUI]
Hey, Junichi.
Oh, hey there, Yui.
Come on, let's blow
this popsicle stand.
[YUKANA]
Right, sorry! Coming!
So, what? Does the teacher
need our help again today?
Uh-uh.
This time I have a personal
favor to ask of you.
[JUNICHI]
Uhh...
[YUI]
Do you mind?
No, I guess not.
Uh, you're touching--
Come with me.
[JUNICHI gasps]
With you where?
[YUI]
Somewhere a bit more private.
[gasping]
[JUNICHI]
Well, this is private.
[YUI] Normally, students
aren't allowed up here,
but I got permission, so don't
worry about getting in trouble.
So what was that favor
you wanted to ask me for?
Yui, what's--?
[YUI]
I just can't take it anymore.
Huh?
[YUI] And you know,
it's all your fault.
What the--? It's my fault?!
[YUI] Because every time
I start to think about you,
it drives me crazy.
When I spend my entire lunch
period just staring at you
while you talk with
all of your friends.
When we're running
errands for the teacher.
And... even right now.
[screams]
[JUNICHI]
What the hell is going on?
Is Yui trying to say that
she's crushing on me?
That she's in love with me?
No, no, no, no, no!
That can't be true!
But bringing me up
here like this,
and the way she's been
talking, is it possible?
This is hard to say,
but here goes.
I-I like you.
Like a lot.
And, well, I was kinda hoping
you'd go out with me.
Really? You want me?
[YUI] Of course, I'd want you
to break up with Yukana first.
I want you to break up with her,
so you can go out with me.
I want you. I want you to
be mine, and mine alone!
[JUNICHI]
Yeah, but...
The thing is...
...I really like Yukana.
Aw, you like me?
[JUNICHI]
I'm sorry! Really, I am!
And I can't even begin
to tell you how shocked
and unbelievably ecstatic
I am that a girl
as ridiculously as cute as you
would ever ask me out, but--
I can't.
[YUI]
You're just a dog.
[JUNICHI]
Eh?
[YUI growls]
You're a flea-bitten, butt
sniffing, ball-sack-licking dog!
Why won't you obey me and
do what I tell you to do?
You're just a dog!
I don't like this shit!
I don't like this one bit!
[screams]
[JUNICHI]
Uh... What now?
All I ask is that you pay
attention to me, doggy!
I'm your damn master, doggy!
I'm your frickin owner, doggy!
You can't just go around
wagging your stupid tail
for every bitch you see!
[laughs]
[JUNICHI]
Woof.
Okay. So, um...
[JUNICHI]
"Doggy"?
Why do these girls keep
comparing me to a freaking dog?
I know how to make you
listen to me, doggy,
if you're just gonna keep
on being disobedient
and pissing all over my carpet!
Huh?
With this!
[JUNICHI]
Uh. Hey, that's--!
[YUI laughs]
[YUI] Bingo! It's from
our date at the café.
I was recording us
the whole time!
[YUI]
Don't try this at home.
Aw, maybe I should just
show this to Yukana.
What do you think about that?
Huh? Think she'll like it?
Hey, no, wait! Please
don't show her that, Yui!
All right, well, then just
go out with me. Okay?
If you do, I'll delete the file.
[JUNICHI] Damn it!
Either way, I'm screwed!
[RANKO]
Hold it right there!
[JUNICHI]
Ranko? And the action pervs?
[ALL]
Super Friends!
[JUNICHI] Hey, guys, be careful!
You're really high up!
[thudding]
We just heard everything.
Awfully arrogant for a girl
who still rocks a training
bra, aren't you?
'Scuse me? What is wrong
with you people?
This isn't your beeswax,
so buzz off!
Now, now, no need
to get testy.
We just wanna join in the fun.
You have got to be kidding me.
Y'know, I have permission
to be up here,
but otherwise, the
roof is off-limits.
So piss off, ho!
What the eff?
Aw, calm down, girlie.
All I want is to be part
of your "royal guard."
[gasps]
Mistress Boa.
[yelps]
Where did you hear that name?
Who knows?
This isn't over, ho-bag.
I will destroy you.
Heh.
Fine.
Take it.
How much do you three know?
We're well informed.
But you have nothing
to worry about.
[KEIGO]
The three of us are...
[MINORU]
...extremely tight-lipped.
What did you say?
Nothing you need to worry
about, Mister Virgin.
Okay.
The only thing I care about is
keeping Yukana happy, got it?
[YUKANA]
Junichi!
[JUNICHI]
Yukana!
[YUKANA]
Come on, walk me home.
[JUNICHI]
Huh, wasn't it just yesterday
she wanted to go
home without me?
[YUKANA]
So were you with Yui again?
Uh.
Well, she's been asking
me for help a lot lately,
so I was just helping her out.
Yeah, but that's all it was!
Any favors I granted were
of the non-sexual variety!
[YUKANA]
Yeah. I know that.
You're, like, totally head over
heels for me, aren't you?
So yeah, you'd have to be
a moron to cheat on this.
You're amazing!
[YUI]
Stupid sprayed-on tan bitch!
I was so close! But whatever,
I'm not giving up!
[STYLIST A]
Oh, girl, that color looks
straight-up fierce on you.
You'll be beating boys
off left and right.
[giggles]
[YUI] This is Bwat Channel.
I'll be your host today!
[AYUMI]
Hi, guys, Ayumi here!
[KOKORO]
And Kokoro!
[AYUMI]
You're not the host!
[KOKORO] Yeah, we already
don't get enough lines!
[YUI] You guys had a
couple of lines today.
Not as many as me--
[AYUMI]
Titless twat.
[YUI]
You two don't have 'em either!
[AYUMI, KOKORO]
Damn it!
We need the animators to
draw us bigger boobs, stat!