Throw down your bow.
You may call me
Eleonora Viltaria.
Your turn.
Lord Tigrevurmud Vorn.
[ELEN] Very well.
From this day forward,
you are now my property.
[TIGRE] Bertrand!
Lord Mashas!
The battle.
It was terrible.
[BRUNE SOLDIERS yell]
So that's a War Maiden.
[TIGRE] From the sound of it,
I've got five shots.
[gasps]
[ZHCTED KNIGHT] The last
Brunish survivor's mine!
[ZHCTED KNIGHT yells]
Aw, rats, come on.
I could have used that horse
to ride out of here.
Seven knights.
[TIGRE] That hair.
The War Maiden.
If I kill her
right now myself,
perhaps they'll stop hunting
Brunish survivors.
All right!
[TIGRE] Range,
three hundred alsins.
Easy.
Guide my arrow, Eris,
Goddess of Wind.
[ELEN] Throw down your bow.
[BRUNE SOLDIERS chattering]
[NARRATOR]
War had broken out
between the Kingdoms
of Brune and Zhcted.
And the Dinant Plains that
lay between the two lands
would see the decisive battle.
So it was,
that the Brunish Army,
with an overwhelming advantage
in numbers, established camp.
There wasn't a man among them
who thought they could lose.
Of course.
[ZION ENTOURAGE laughs]
Well. I didn't know
you'd be here, Vorn.
My greetings from
one lord to another.
Lord Zion Thenardier.
I, too, have answered His
Majesty's call to defeat--
[ZION] Such a demure
way of talking back.
What good are you here
among men like us?
[ZION] The poor fool
is built like a feather
and covered in rags!
[ZION ENTOURAGE 1A]
Leather armor!
[ZION ENTOURAGE 1B]
Shouldn't a nobleman
at least dress the part?
And that bow. Heh, heh.
The weapon of a peasant!
[ZION yells]
[ZION ENTOURAGE 1A]
No, Lord Zion!
[ZION ENTOURAGE 1B]
Are you hurt?
What gives you the right
to bend my bow?
You're pathetic!
A bow and arrow
is a coward's weapon.
[ZION] Oh, Vorn.
Why don't you admit the
reason you use a bow
is because you're not strong
enough to wield a real weapon.
You're a boy, pretending
to be a soldier.
And having an old man
for an attendant
only makes you that
much more of a disgrace.
In battle, there's only
one way to defend Brune.
You should be training
with a man's weapon.
Maybe this can wait.
I hate to interrupt
this eloquent lecture,
but they're handing out the
evening's wine rations now.
And I assume your talking
has made you quite thirsty.
Go fill your goblet, please.
I appreciate the assist.
Thanks, Lord Mashas.
[MASHAS]
Happy to do so.
Guess I couldn't help
escalating things, but...
You saved me from a nasty fight.
[NOBLEMAN 1A] If you ask me,
I envy Duke Ganelon.
[NOBLEMAN 1B]
What? Why?
For using this war as
a pretense to raise taxes.
And for taking his
enemies' daughters.
That's true. Duke Thenardier's
just as crafty, making subjects
donate their liquor as
a "sacrifice to the gods."
And both are torching the homes
of anyone who holds out.
That's nothing, I've heard that
to set an example to others,
Duke Thenardier's forcing family
members to take up swords
and fight to the death.
How entertaining!
[NOBLEMEN laugh]
Not worth it.
[TIGRE] Are those stories
they're telling true?
The men in question
wouldn't deny it.
It's news to you
because you don't travel
through the middle of
the Kingdom very often.
And the King?
[MASHAS] His Majesty has
something in mind for them,
I'm sure.
Like a punishment?
And even if he can't,
I'm sure in time Prince Regnas
will possess the strength.
[groans]
Huh?
[TIGRE chokes]
You've been sleeping
long enough.
Is it late?
[LIM] It's almost noon.
That's a strange way
of waking people up.
[LIM] Well having
to wake a slave
by shoving a sword down his
throat is a first for me, too.
How can you lose a battle,
become a prisoner,
and still sleep without
a care in the world?
It's one of my
magic powers.
[TIGRE] So, this is
the Kingdom of Zhcted?
[LIM] Lady Eleonora
would like to see you.
[TITTA] What?!
No.
But how could Zhcted
capture him so easily?
We suffered a total
rout in a sneak attack.
Tigre couldn't flee in time,
but he fought well.
[TITTA]
But, I thought that
I heard our forces outnumbered
Zhcted five to one!
How could we lose
so decisively?
[MASHAS] You're right.
We had an army twenty-five
thousand strong
to only their five thousand.
It was a mighty force
His Majesty had assembled
in honor of the Prince's
debut campaign.
Lord Tigre was so ready.
He had one hundred brave banner
men following him into battle.
[BERTRAND] The battle
wasn't the only thing lost.
Of those hundred men, seven
are dead and thirty injured.
[TITTA gasps]
And most of those were trampled
by our own fleeing allies.
We received the following
demand from the enemy leader:
Unless we deliver a ransom
within fifty days,
Tigre will become Zhicted's
property forever.
How much do they want?
Even if it's exorbitant,
I'm sure we can get
the villagers to chip in!
[MASHAS] They demand three
times the yearly revenue
of the province of Alsace,
or something of
comparable value.
[gasps]
[TIGRE] Be reasonable.
That's way too high.
[ELEN] Too bad.
[TIGRE sighs]
The Kingdom of Brune
has fifty days to comply
with our ransom demand
after receiving it.
Time's a-wasting.
If the full amount
we've requested
is not delivered to me,
in accordance with the treaty.
You will officially
become my property,
for me to do with as I see fit.
This I swear in
the name of Radegast,
god of honor and contracts.
Well, all right.
This is why you stuck your sword
in my mouth and brought me here.
So I could hear your crazy
greed with my own ears.
Now, now.
There's more to our
talking than ransom.
I have something special
only you can do for me.
[SPECTATORS groaning]
[SPECTATOR 1A]
That's two now that he's missed!
You better be taking
this seriously.
I am, don't worry.
Is this your first time
with a bow, sir?
[laughing]
Now that's cutting
with a knife, Ryurik.
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1D]
Of all the prisoners,
why would the War Maiden
bring back this weakling?
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1E]
Looks like he's gonna keep
embarrassing himself!
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1F]
Useless and a glutton...
This entire
demonstration is a farce.
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1G] His first
shot was way too short.
His second was way too long.
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1H]
That means on his third try,
he'll shoot himself
in the foot! Ha ha ha!
I've got a feel for
this bow's limits.
Here goes.
Huh?
Get down! Assassin!
Arifal!
I want him skinned alive!
I mean no insult, but
can they take him alive?
Who do you think you are
telling me what to do here?!
[TIGRE] Fine,
then I'll hit his foot.
[ASSASSIN gasps]
[ASSASSIN yells]
His aim is unreal!
And he did it with
a bad bow, too!
[ASSASSIN groaning]
He hit a moving target from well
over three hundred alsins away.
[TIGRE]
Just so we're clear,
do you want me to keep shooting?
I think I've seen enough.
You're quite a talent,
Lord Tigrevurmud Vorn.
[ELEN]
My apologies for yesterday.
Wait, for what?
The bow they gave you.
It was never my intention
for you to receive one
that shoddily constructed.
So. you weren't trying
to make me look bad,
it was shoddy Zhcted
craftsmanship.
[ELEN] No.
The three men who made the bow
did want to sabotage you.
I'll have them beheaded.
Whoa, hold on!
It was a harmless prank.
No one got hurt!
That was more than a prank.
They wanted to humiliate you!
And bring dishonor to your
people and your family!
Custom demands that they pay for
this scheme with their lives!
Then I beg you.
Please show them mercy.
[ELEN sighs]
[ELEN] This one time.
So, what was the point
of having me show off my
skills in the first place?
[ELEN giggles]
You see, she...
[ZHCTED SOLDIERS fighting]
The War Maiden fell
for me at first sight!
That's right. You could
call it battlefield passion,
an affection that only
comes between close enemies.
You know how people love
gossiping about palace intrigue.
And they're not
wrong to do so.
I really am mad
for you, you know!
[TIGRE] For me?
Not for your looks
or personality!
I'm attracted to your skill
with the bow and arrow.
But anyway.
I guess some of my men
heard the gossip
and were feeling
a bit jealous of you.
Instead of finding a place
for you by my side,
they'd rather I kill you!
[gasps]
Killing him would probably
be the easiest thing.
But that's just my opinion.
[ELEN] The army ranks
are full of hot heads.
I thought having you
show off your skills
would be the quickest way to
change their opinions of you.
Ultimately, it was effective.
And one more thing,
since I'm being honest.
Beyond your bow skills,
the reason I took you prisoner
at the Dinant Plains
was not for a ransom.
Mostly, it was because
I found you, entertaining.
Entertaining how?
In a battle?
Despite the win, that battle
was still nasty business.
As well as being a
complete and total waste.
[ELEN] We numbered
just five thousand,
against your side's twenty-five.
I braced myself for
a brutal battle.
[ELEN] Attack! Yah!
[ELEN] From the start
of our charge,
the battle should have
gone on a day.
[TIGRE] You say that
like you're disappointed!
I prepared a number of
plans I was excited to try!
And yet, your side
collapsed from my first plan
right as the battle began!
Your first plan, huh?
Nighttime sneak attack.
Thanks to the reconnaissance
our scouts had carried out,
we surprised the
Brunish rearguard
and scattered the troops.
In that melee, the Brunish
Prince was killed.
[TIGRE]
You mean Prince Regnas?!
Were you two close friends?
[TIGRE]
Not at all.
I only met him
once in my whole life.
[ELEN] Do you hold
his death against me?
[TIGRE] It happened in battle.
I killed some of your men
myself, you know.
Yes, I'm sure.
Once news of his
death got around,
the Brunish army came
apart at the seams.
[ELEN] I didn't want them
to regroup for another day,
so I pursued, cutting
them down as they fled.
And so it was all my
great plans went unused.
But in that moment,
you flew onto the scene.
In spite of
your allegiances,
I didn't want to kill you.
Brune's army turned out
to be a paper tiger.
But you kept your courage
and stayed in the fight,
even tried to shoot me
down with your bow!
I've a weakness
for such mettle.
So I brought you to
Leitmeritz, in Zhcted.
Lim, are you holding
a grudge against him
for what happened
on the battlefield?
I promise, the battle had
nothing to do with it.
[TIGRE] Hm?
I'm not sure I believe that.
Remember that first
horse you shot down?
Lim was the rider.
Why don't we start over?
I am the War Maiden's
bodyguard, Limalisha.
Count Tigrevurmud Vorn,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
Uh. Hello.
You know, if I'm
being honest, your name,
it sounds like a mouthful
for a traditional Brunishman.
Is there a fun story behind it?
Well, it's the name of
one of my ancestors.
If it's too hard to say,
you can always call me "Tigre."
Tigre it is!
And feel free
to call me "Elen."
I also think
that we should--
[LIM]
Lady Eleonora!
Tigre, will you
serve under me?
I will treat you as a Count,
just as you were in Brune.
And valor you show in combat
will be honored like that
of any other pure born
Zhcted warrior.
Heh. Thanks, but no.
I'm honored you would ask.
And I'm pretty sure an offer
like this would never happen
if the roles were
reversed in Brune.
So why are you refusing
to take my hand?
[TIGRE] I already have a home
I need to get back to.
One I swore to protect.
Alsace.
[TIGRE] It's a Brunish province
I inherited from my father.
Oh, Lord Tigre.
Don't die on me.
[TIGRE chuckles]
[TIGRE] You must stop shaving
your head, Ryurik.
That shiny orb is going
to blind somebody!
Plus, the look's not doing your
handsome features any favors.
I'll say this for
the last time!
For trying to embarrass
you on the archery range,
the War Maiden made me sacrifice
my gorgeous hair as penance!
By all rights, my head
should be on the chopping block!
But Lord Tigrevurmud Vorn,
since I've been allowed to live,
thanks in part to you, I shall
continue to make this offering!
And I honestly admire
your bow skill.
it puts my own
abilities to shame.
You're a master, and I,
a foolish novice
who tried to humiliate you.
Okay...
So please, don't ask me
to cease my penance!
[TIGRE] You can stand up now!
I'm sorry I brought it up!
There they go again.
I've never seen a man
as polite as Master Ryurik.
Agreed. And Lord
Tigrevurmud's marksmanship
does deserve that praise.
He's very impressive!
And cute!
I eat this every day
and it's always great!
I sometimes forget
how foreign you are.
There's nothing special
about this food;
it's standard soldier fare.
And that's the best part!
Whenever I get back home,
it'll be easy enough
for Titta to make!
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1G] How does he
hit with three arrows at once?
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1H]
Maybe he's a magic archer!
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 1I]
Lord Tigre!
Please give us
another lesson soon!
Of course!
I'm finally fitting
in around here.
But a prisoner
is still a prisoner.
[TIGRE] Is that...?
A baby Dragon?
I've never seen one.
[ELEN] That's my pet.
His name is Lunie.
[ELEN] Hello.
Sorry! I didn't see anything!
I had found this place
when walking around before.
I didn't think anyone
else used it, so...
[ELEN] There's nothing
to be sorry about.
After all, you came here
to bathe, too, right?
Now turn around and
look me in the eyes.
So here in your country
it's custom for men and women
to take baths in
front of each other?
Actually, it's not.
I'm not saying I'm
not embarrassed.
But I'm... a war
maiden, aren't I?
If I'm caught off
guard--even naked--
I can't run away and cower
like a shy country girl.
Even if deep down, my brain's
telling me to do just that!
[ELEN chuckles]
I want you, Lord Tigre.
This place is...
just so different.
She says she wants me.
Well...
[knocking]
Huh?
The guards have seized an old
man with a Brunish accent.
[TIGRE] Bertrand!
[BERTRAND gasps]
Young Master!
[BERTRAND]
Thank goodness you're safe!
So you do know
this sad old man!
Yes, of course I do!
Bertrand's been my attendant
since I was just a kid!
[BERTRAND] My lord,
there's no time to reminisce.
Huh?
Thenardier has gathered a force
and is marching on your
province of Alsace!
They number three thousand men!
He's doing what?!
[RYURIK]
Get back here!
You can't leave!
You're our prisoner!
Good evening, Tigre.
Where do you think you're going?
Get out of my way.
[ELEN] You may as well
meet your end here.
[ELEN] Episode 2:
"The Return Home."
Watch it.