[LIM]
While fighting here in Alsace,
we struck down
three hundred knights.
Those who managed to
retreat and evade our pursuit
are probably regrouping with
the main Thenardier force
as we speak.
[ELEN] What about
their commander, Lord Zion?
[LIM] Unfortunately, he's one
of the men who escaped.
[ELEN]
Damn... Missed opportunity.
If we believe that his force
started at three thousand,
that means they're still
twenty-seven hundred strong.
The bare minimum
needed to protect this town
is one hundred...
That leaves us just
nine hundred for battle.
Bottom line they still
outnumber us three to one.
[ELEN] How far do you think
Zion will flee?
Probably to here,
in the Molsheim Plains.
The terrain will help
make their knights
more effective in combat.
[ELEN] Good. Then that's
where we shall meet them.
They'll pay for
what they've done.
Let's finish the job.
Wait, that was a
Zhcted Army? That's insane.
What would they be doing
all the way over here?
[ZION] Vorn.
Wait a second, now I see it...
It's him!
He's the one behind this!
That inexperienced,
arrow-loving little boy.
[ZION growling]
[items clattering]
Send out more scouts!
They're not to return
until they know the size
of the Zhcted Army!
[ZION AIDES]
Sir!
Argh! And I'm certain he's the
one who betrayed our position
at the Dinant Plains, too...
That traitorous,
arrow-shooting pink-haired rat!
[groaning in pain]
You watch, Vorn...
You're done disrespecting me.
[NARRATOR] Lord Zion Thenardier
divided his remaining
twenty-seven hundred men
into three groups.
The first numbered
seven hundred.
These were light infantry,
armed with bows and spears.
The second group was comprised
of one thousand heavy knights,
in steel plate armor
and carrying lances.
The last thousand formed
the main battle force.
A traditional Brunish company
trained to fight and win
on grassy plains.
And then there were
his trump cards...
...Zion's two dragons.
[TITTA] If it's frayed,
we'll weave it again!
We're collecting rope!
It's to fight Thenardier!
[WOMAN 3A]
Good luck!
Thank you!
Every little bit helps!
[WOMAN 3B] Lord Tigre
will put it all to good use.
[WOMAN 3C]
Such a smart lad.
That'll show those
Thenardier goons
not to mess with Alsace.
Whatever we can do to
help Lord Tigre, we will.
[TITTA]
Thanks for your loyalty!
[ELEN] Tigre and I will lead
a company of four hundred men.
Lim, you're in command
of the other five hundred.
Hold out for an opening,
and then hit them hard.
Anything you'd like to change?
Well, I think we
could use some rope.
Doesn't matter
if it's old or frayed;
we'll double it up.
I just need a lot.
Some rope, okay.
[TITTA] I can handle that,
no problem!
Are you sure?
I can ask
all the townspeople...
I'm happy to help!
I'm not going to say no!
Um, are you...
Are you and Lord Tigre...
...in... some...
[TITTA] Are you and
Lord Tigre in some kind of
secret romantic
relationship, my Lady?
[ELEN] Well, he does
sort of belong to me now.
[TITTA gasps]
Yes, she's right.
Technically.
For the time being.
[ELEN] Oh, no.
Not just for the time being!
By the terms of the treaty,
you belong to me, in perpetuity!
[TIGRE] All right.
That may be true on paper,
but I think we can all
agree beating Zion
--comes first right now.
--I...
I won't be outdone by her!
[TITTA sobbing]
[BERTRAND chuckles]
She won't be outdone.
[LIM] Lady Eleonora...
Right, back to business.
[TIGRE] In that case,
what will you do with those
spare horses we brought?
Spare horses?
[LIM] We were planning to leave
them in the town of Selestat.
Is that a problem?
No, but I may have
a better use for them.
For a Brunishman,
he does have interesting ideas.
[BERTRAND] Young master!
You're here, at last!
Oh, be nice!
[BERTRAND] Hahaha!
Being your arrow boy means
I can't even wield a sword!
[TIGRE] Don't worry!
As long as you
remain behind us,
you won't be on the
stabbing end of anything.
Isn't that right?
That's right!
Of course, I won't
let you get hurt, either...
As long as I'm in this fight!
[NARRATOR]
Although outnumbered by enemies,
Lady Eleonora
ordered four hundred
of her mounted knights
to hit the
Thenardier front lines.
And she, along with Lord Tigre,
will lead the charge.
The two armies march
toward one another--
A clash of arms,
a field of blood,
mere seconds away.
Are you scared?
Sure, a little.
But I'm more afraid
that we might lose.
That's good to hear.
I'm the same.
Zhcted attack!
[ZHCTED ARMY yelling]
Ready, Arifal?
Ha!
[ZHCTED ARMY yelling]
I've never seen anyone
as talented with a weapon
as you are with that bow!
Well, I'm surprised
to hear you say that!
[ELEN] It's a compliment!
I'm being sincere!
[SOLDIERS groaning in pain]
Danseuse of the Sword...
Wind Princess
of the Silver Flash...
We can't afford to be
outdone, Bertrand!
[BERTRAND] Aye!
Don't let up! Ha!
[THENARDIER COMMANDER] This is
revenge for the Dinant Plains!
Young master!
[HORSES neighing]
[roaring]
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 3C]
My gods!
[ZHCTED SOLDIER 3D]
It's a dragon!
Land dragon,
and it's brass-colored.
I can't imagine
trying to tame one of those.
[NARRATOR] The Thenardier forces
march their land dragon ahead,
using knights to
bolster their flanks.
Hemmed in, the Zhcted
cavalry can't pass the beast.
The plains soon
fill with their blood
and echo with their screams.
[roaring]
The eye...
Like armor...
[ZION laughs]
Vorn! Your arrows
can't save you now!
That dragon is going
to crush your skull
and rip your limbs off!
That is your fate as a traitor.
[THENARDIER SCOUT 3A]
My lord!
They're ambushing the
second column's flank!
Haha!
Your Dinant Plains tricks
won't work this time!
Send four hundred men
from the flying column!
[LIM] Don't let up!
It's going just as we planned!
[NARRATOR] Dividing the
Zhcted army in two pays off.
Lim charges four hundred men
into the Thenardier flank.
In the melee,
a path clears for Elen
to face down the
land dragon, one-on-one.
I didn't expect
to fight a dragon,
so to mark the big day...
I'll show you
a very special move.
Elen, what...?
[roars]
Mow down, air and all!
Ley... Admos!
Now let's finish this battle.
Well, that was
something I didn't expect.
Of course you didn't.
I don't play all
of my cards at once.
It's quite forceful, so
I don't use it around people
if I can avoid it.
The Ley... Admos.
Lim, the enemy is moving forces
from its flying column.
Then that's our cue to
fall back, just as we planned.
Yes, ma'am!
[NARRATOR]
Zion sends four hundred men
to form a fast-moving
infantry brigade
known as a "flying column."
In response,
Lim denies them a fight,
and withdraws her
own force to the hills.
[THENARDIER SOLDIER 3L]
We have them on the run!
[THENARDIER CHIEF 3A]
Cut down those fools,
and the battle will be ours!
[LIM] Now!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
You fall down
because you only look
at who you're fighting,
not where.
[LIM] Our foreign army wouldn't
have collected what we did
had Zion not treated his
fellow Brunishmen so poorly.
Lord Tigrevurmud Vorn
has a close connection with
the common folk of Alsace.
And there's one more
who trusts him...
It's almost time.
That's right.
It's time for an ambush.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[THENARDIER SCOUT 3B] Enemy
forces are behind us!
A whole other army...
two thousand!
Two thousand men?
I have barely six hundred
left in my main force!
We're cut off in the rear
and outnumbered.
There's still hope.
Send in the flying dragon!
Do what?
You idiot!
She made mincemeat
out of the land dragon!
Split it just like an apple!
I'm not going to watch her
do that to this one, too!
After all, it's me my father
will blame, not you!
Think, Zion Thenardier,
you can do this.
What is a
commander's first duty?
The bravest thing I
can do is to protect the...
That's it! Save myself!
Bring the second column around!
We retreat, now.
Lord Zion, Sir,
give us a chance
to fight them off.
If our knights on the front
line can hold their ground
long enough for us
to regroup and strike,
we could still--
[ZION] Shut up!
Oww! Oww! Oww!
Sir, not in front of the men.
Get the knights to
stand down, right away!
Do it!
[NARRATOR] What Zion
had not realized--
No, what he could not realize,
was that the enemy troops to his
rear were just one hundred men.
It was the horses that
numbered two thousand.
Lord Tigre used the
terrain and setting sun
to create the illusion
of reinforcements.
Did you say retreat?
We can still win this battle!
What the hell's
gotten into them?
Sir, there's a huge enemy force
approaching from behind!
This order comes down
from Lord Zion himself!
That idiot son
is an embarrassment!
[NARRATOR] Honor and duty
meant the knights
of the House of Thenardier
had no choice but to obey.
And with their sudden
pullback from the frontlines,
The momentum shifts
in Elen and Tigre's favor.
[THENARDIER SCOUT 3A]
They've broken through
the second knight column!
[THENARDIER SCOUT 3B]
The main force
is starting to buckle, too!
All our lines are collapsing!
Why didn't he send the dragon?
This is a bad dream!
It's the only explanation!
How else could that Vorn,
a stupid arrogant boy,
defeat me?
[horses approaching]
And now he's here!
You started this fight!
You don't get to run away!
Zion Thenardier!
[ZION] Run away?
Don't be ridiculous.
How could you
betray your country?
You led the Zhcted army right
into the Brunish heartland!
You really are descended
from nothing but
illiterate, cowardly huntsmen!
If you're blaming people,
start with yourself!
[ZION] How dare you!
You hurt your own
innocent countrymen,
burn their homes,
steal their property.
You're not a lord,
you're just a thief!
My own countrymen?
And what about those fools?
They're just like plants.
I can cut them down all I want
and they'll grow right back.
So why the hell do you care?
That bastard.
You're not helping
your cause, Lord Zion.
But it doesn't matter.
You're unforgivable.
You marched your
army onto my land,
tormented my people!
Disrespect me?
You've got more
nerve than sense.
Vorn, I challenge you to a duel!
You wanted a fight, didn't you?
Don't try to run away.
He's gone insane.
[ELEN] Wait, Tigre!
You're not dueling him!
All right...
This battle is yours
and yours alone.
[ZION]
Where's your weapon, traitor?
I'm sure your new
friends in the Zhcted army
would be happy to
loan you a spear or a sword.
Here's the only weapon I need!
[ZION] Is this a joke to you?
You can't think you'll win a
duel with just a bow and arrow!
It's supposed to be one-on-one,
with swords, a long range--
[TIGRE] Let's put it to a test.
Serious?
A-ha! You see?
It's not for dueling!
[ZION] Keep on wasting
those arrows, dummy!
[ZION laughing]
You're boring me, Vorn!
It's impossible
to have a real duel
as long as you insist on
using that coward's weapon.
I'm ending this
charade and your life.
Your head is going on my lance!
Yah!
[ZION] You had no
honor in life, Vorn,
and you'll get none in death!
This can't be!
I hate you, bastard!
[ZION yelling in pain]
Young master...
To hit that same
spot on the shield,
only as a moving target...
Such a spectacle makes me
want him even more...
[groaning in pain]
[high-pitched wailing]
[THENARDIER SOLDIER 3M]
Save Lord Zion!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ELEN] Protect Lord Tigre!
I wasn't sure
how that would go.
Well, neither was I.
You and your
precious Alsace
can enjoy the privilege of being
crushed under my father's boot!
I've got better things
to do than die fighting you!
[ZION laughs]
He's climbing
too high and fast
for my wind blades to reach.
[TIGRE] Are we just
going to stand here?
Watch him fly away?
[MYSTERIOUS FEMALE VOICE]
Shoot the dragon.
I'll say it again...
[MYSTERIOUS FEMALE VOICE]
Shoot the dragon.
[TIGRE] Did you just talk?
Are you giving
Tigre's bow your strength?
[ZION yelling]
[ELEN] Tigrevurmud Vorn
has killed Zion Thenardier!
The battle is won!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[NARRATOR]
With its commander's death,
the Thenardier Army
lost its will to fight,
and melted away
into the countryside.
And so it was,
that Alsace was
successfully defended.
[LIM] I very well couldn't turn
away a War Maiden now could I?
[LIM] Episode 4: "Michelia."
Please watch.