[ZION]
You summoned me, Father?
There's something I'd
like you to handle for me,
if you're up to the task.
[THENARDIER] Take three
thousand of our troops
and march them towards Alsace.
[ZION] Alsace?
The territory of
that miserable Vorn
who got himself taken prisoner?
Why would I--
[THENARDIER]
I have for you...
...a parting gift of sorts.
[roars]
[laughs]
[DREKAVAC] We're not quite done
breaking them in yet.
But if you take them
into battle today,
they will perform magnificently.
I get my own dragons?
[laughs]
How exciting!
You just watch me, Vorn...
I'm going to burn your precious
homeland down to the ground!
Good evening, Tigre.
Where do you think you're going?
Get out of my way.
So that's a Zhcted
war maiden?
Correct.
She is our mistress...
Wind Princess of
the Silver Flash,
also known as Danseuse
of the Sword...
Lady Eleonora Viltaria.
[ELEN] What?
Do you have a problem with
the way I'm dressed?
And after I put on some clothes
just so you could look at me
without blushing
like a schoolboy.
I have to get back to
Alsace. It's urgent!
[ELEN] Have you forgotten
your situation, milord?
[TIGRE] Thenardier's
attacking my homeland!
If I don't go now,
it'll be too late!
Please let me go!
Once I save them,
I'll come back. I promise!
[ELEN] And when you get to
Alsace, what will you do?
What'll I do?
I'll protect the province,
of course!
Yes, but how?
[TIGRE]
How...? Uh...
I know that you're
very good with a bow...
...but how much can
you do on your own?
Despite all your
skill and resolve,
you can't stop a force
of three thousand.
It's just a fool's errand.
I'm aware.
[ELEN] And yet you
still want to go?
Yes, I must!
Maybe there's
something I can do!
What can a reckless
and impulsive man
like you possibly do?
[TIGRE gasps]
[ELEN] As you know, the penalty
for running away is death.
If you're so eager to die,
you may as well
meet your end here.
Dying in Leitmeritz
would be no different
than dying in Alsace, after all.
So I can't leave?
You won't allow me to?
[sighs]
Do you even understand why
I'm so upset about this?
[ELEN] Why not use your wits?
At Dinant, you tried to turn
things to your advantage.
And though you failed, at least
you were clever about it.
But here in this instance,
you'd act on emotion,
without thought, even though
it means certain death.
I don't know what
else to tell you.
[gasps]
[TIGRE] Why hasn't she
just run me through?
She could have commanded
Ryurik and the others
to apprehend me...
But she hasn't.
Young Master...
[TIGRE] Perhaps Elen...
...is trying to offer me
an opportunity.
Then help me.
[TIGRE] Please...
Lend me your army.
[ELEN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Is he crazy?
He's a hostage!
[ELEN chuckles]
[ELEN laughing]
[laughing continues]
You're too much.
That was so stupidly brazen,
it's actually refreshing.
[ELEN] You want me to
lend you an army?
Very well...
But of course it's
going to cost you.
The price?
All of Alsace.
If you save her, she's yours,
as long as you promise
to rule her fairly
and protect her people.
What, no haggling? Huh.
[ELEN]
It's settled!
Raise the Zirnitra banners!
On to battle!
[ZHCTED SOLDIERS yelling]
[LIM] I was taken aback.
It took some nerve asking you
to supply him with troops.
Seems he's defied
both our expectations.
[ELEN] You predicted that
Tigre would challenge me
to an archery contest.
Meanwhile...
I thought that he'd ask me to
make him one of my attendants.
And considering he
hasn't made that request,
it would appear
you lost the wager.
I'm afraid you were wrong
about him, my Lady.
But of course, I was, as well.
Not sure it still counts as
a bet if neither of us is right.
[knocking]
He's here!
[ELEN] You're going into
battle dressed like that?
You do realize you're basically
the commander of
an army now, right?
Well, this is
all that I have.
[ELEN] Uh...
[LIM] Ugh, you are a mess.
Here, this'll have to do.
We're out of time.
But we can at least neaten
up your hair a little
so you don't look quite
so disheveled.
[TIGRE] Uh, thank you...
[ELEN chuckles]
Here, I wanna help!!
[TIGRE] Hey, is this
really necessary?
[ELEN]
Don't fight it!
[TIGRE]
[ELEN]
Well, I guess that's it.
Hmm? What's wrong?
I know you're
probably overwhelmed
with appreciation right now,
but you could say something...
Like, "How beautiful!"
I've wanted to say
that ever since
I first saw you.
Their army...
It's much larger!
Can we really beat them?
Yes, but they don't
know the land...
Nobody from their House
has been to Alsace in ages!
And that does matter...
Trust me!
I know the province like
the back of my hand!
We have that
going for us.
All right, then, let's win this!
That's it...
Slowly, so they can
get a good look.
Think long and hard about
whether you side with
the House of Thenardier
or the House of Ganelon...
All you citizens of Brune!
[ZION laughs maniacally]
[STEED] So that's the reason
you sent Lord Zion to Alsace...
Now that Prince Regnas
has been struck down,
it's left a power vacuum
with no successor
capable of ruling as king.
Soon, control of Brune
will be mine,
or it will all go to Ganelon.
The struggle between us
is only a matter of time.
[THENARDIER] Alsace...
It's a land of no
importance or value
and too far removed from
the center of things...
But Ganelon may try to take it,
and that's reason enough.
So now you'll
reduce it to ashes?
Still, sending three
thousand soldiers
to such a remote location...
Not to mention the dragons...
[THENARDIER] I'm sending a
message to the weaker provinces.
And besides,
I wanted the dragons
to become accustomed to Zion.
[ALSACE SOLDIER 2A] Head for
the mountains or the woods!
[TITTA]
Take refuge in the temple!
You'll be safe! No one
would dare attack you there!
I'll find a way to halt
Ganehlon's movement,
whatever it takes.
Bertrand, you should
go to Zhcted.
Fill Tigre in so he knows
what's going on here.
Just leave it to me.
I won't return without
the young master.
Titta, you go work
with the soldiers
to help evacuate
all the residents.
Send the strong to
the mountains or woods,
everyone else to the temple.
Not even Thenardier would dare
make an enemy of
the temple at this point.
Yes!
Go on, Titta...
Shouldn't you be leaving
the city, as well?
No, I'm staying here.
I want to be at Lord Tigre's
door to greet him...
when he returns home.
[TIGRE sighs]
[TIGRE] Every time I look
at that bow, I think,
"Something about it
just feels so ostentatious."
Lord Tigre,
don't think like that.
It's a precious family heirloom,
left to you by your ancestors.
Which is why I
pay my respects.
As I did today, and every day.
[gasps]
[TIGRE] It's been two years
now since Father died.
I'm still not much
of a feudal lord,
but at least I've got Bertrand
here, and you, Titta.
It's only because of you two
that we're getting by
as well as we are.
Whoa, What's come over
you all of a sudden today?
Oh no!
Are you feeling all right?
I'm grateful.
No, stop!
Don't act so serious!
It makes me feel like something
bad's going to happen...
[TITTA sobbing]
[BERTRAND] The young master
will be here soon.
Though he's probably
catching hell from Titta
right now for sleeping in!
[ALSACE SOLDIERS laugh]
[TITTA] But why, sir?
I don't understand
why you have to go off
and fight in this silly war!
Because His Majesty
called us...
As a count in the
kingdom of Brune
and head of the House
of Vorn, I must.
Yes, but...
It's fine.
The army's huge...
I'm sure they'll just put us all
the way in the rearguard...
I'll come back, I swear.
[TITTA sniffs]
Lord Tigre...
You're coming back...
You're coming back to us,
aren't you? You promised.
[THENARDIER SOLDIERS yelling]
[TITTA] Lord Tigre!
[ZION laughs]
[THENARDIER SOLDIERS yelling]
[VILLAGERS panicking]
[ZION sighs]
With a pathetic town as
flea-bitten as this one,
there's just not enough
thrill in destroying it.
Now, it might be another story
if we could use the dragons,
but I can't disobey my father.
The dragons are not yet
accustomed to all the smells
that are found in villages.
Be sure to keep them
outside the walls.
Are you mad?
Then why am I even
bringing them?
[THENARDIER]
Use your head.
You use the dragons
to scare them,
and not just in Alsace.
This is a warning
to all of Brune.
Go against Thenardier,
and you will be
forfeiting your future!
[ZION] What do you mean
there's nobody in the town?
[THENARDIER SOLDIER 2A]
It appears most of them fled
into the forest, while the rest
are holed up inside the temple.
What would you
like us to do, sir?
Temple's off limits...
If we attack this one,
we'll be inviting all of Brune's
temples to turn against us.
No, leave them be!
[ZION chuckles]
[ZION]
The Vorn home, eh?
No...
Lord Tigre...
Watch over me...
and give me... courage.
[TITTA gasps]
[ZION grunts]
Get out of here.
Ah... well, aren't you
a pretty little thing.
Please, just leave.
Huh?
I'm not sure
I heard you right...
Seems that Vorn imbecile
is terrible at training
his maids, too.
Now, go on, say it again.
Just leave.
What's that?
[gasps]
I said get the hell out of here!
This estate, and everything in
this town belong to Lord Tigre!
So don't you dare lay
a finger on any of it!
You heard me!
Now get out!
Get out of here now!
[ZION sighs]
[ZION laughs]
[TITTA screams]
[ZION] What's wrong?
You should get up and run away
or next time I'll
cut off your legs.
[ZION laughs]
[ZION] Are we done playing
this game of cat and mouse?
Lord Tigre...
Heh! Now what do we have here?
Sounds like the little maid
is harboring secret
feelings for her master...
No, it's not like that!
Lord Tigre...
[ZION] Poor girl, I imagine
your precious Master Vorn
has failed to pay
his ransom, and,
as we speak, is likely
being sold into slavery.
Shall I do the
same with you?
If you're lucky,
perhaps you'll be reunited.
Two slaves together...
You can fulfill your fantasies!
[laughs evilly]
No, you're wrong!
Lord Tigre is coming back!
Now isn't that adorable.
[TITTA yells]
Yes, go ahead, scream
and moan all you like.
You can even call out
his name, I don't mind.
[TITTA] Lord Tigre...
[screams]
[TIGRE] Titta, jump!
Jump now!
[TITTA giggles]
[TIGRE] Titta!
[TIGRE] What the...?
[ELEN] You are quite reckless.
I don't mean to rub
it in or anything,
but if I weren't with you,
you'd be hurting pretty badly.
The wind...
So that's it.
Your power...
[ELEN] That's right.
This sword controls the wind,
and is only wielded
by war maidens.
This is Arifal.
Huh? Seems to have
taken a liking to you.
Ah... Zion...
[ELEN] Zion?
[TIGRE] The eldest son of
the House of Thenardier
and next in line to lead it.
[ELEN] Hmm, so he's
their commander.
Forward!
[ZHCTED SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[TITTA] Lord Tigre!
Yes, Titta?
Lord Tigre!
[TIGRE] Hey, wait a second.
Why were you still here...?
In case...
In case anything were
to happen here...
I at least wanted to be
able to save this for you.
You fool!
You should've gone and
hidden with the rest!
[TITTA] But there was
no way I could do that!
Titta...
You left me here...
It's my duty to watch over
this place while you're away!
So I couldn't just abandon it!
Even though
I was scared...
So scared...
But through it all...
I believed in you.
Thank you.
You're making me jealous...
So she's more of your
type, then, is she?
Lord Tigre, who are
all of these people?
[ZHCTED SOLDIERS gasp]
[TITTA gasps]
Can you fight?
Of course...
Watch me.
Zirnitras!
[ELEN] Charge!
[ZHCTED SOLDIERS yell]
Tigre, come on!
Right!
My bow...
It just happened...
[TITTA] Lord Tigre...
Now is the time.
[URS] Use this bow only
when you truly require it.
I suppose
that's right now.
[ELEN] Don't let even one
soldier escape!
We'll make sure they get
what's coming to them!
Yes, Lord Urs.
the young master's
finally done it...
...picked up the black bow.
[NARRATOR] A black bow,
handed down through the ages,
has finally been taken up
by the young Tigre
as he goes off to battle.
The enemy numbers
three thousand,
his allies, a third of that.
Which side will fortune favor?
[TIGRE] Did you... just talk?
[TIGRE] Episode 3: "Return of
the Magic Marksman."
Enjoy watching.