Hey, watch it! Be careful
with our weapons!
I'm sorry, sir.
[GERARD] I'm going to
need your signature on this.
The Navarre knights will be
buried on the west side
[GERARD] with the
Silver Meteor Storm's fallen
interred on the east
side of the hill.
That sounds fine.
You can do whatever
you want with their effects.
[GERARD] Oh, thank you.
[OLIVIER] The armor is from
the Order of Navarre,
so it'll fetch a good price.
Yes. Don't worry,
I'll put it all to good use.
[GERARD] But you're sure
you won't fight alongside
the Silver Meteor Storm?
[OLIVIER] We can't leave
the western border
unguarded for too long.
It's time for us to return.
I wish the
Silver Meteor Storm luck.
[ROLAND]
I'll go to the capital.
I'll arrange an audience
for you with His Majesty.
You can't!
Lord Mashas almost
got himself killed!
[ROLAND grunts]
As a knight of Brune, I must
try to make things right.
[MASHAS grunts]
[MASHAS]
I admire your resolve.
Speaking of which,
what's keeping Elen?
Not sure.
A messenger from Legnica
just showed up.
I see.
[ROLAND] I'll come back.
[ELEN] I have to return
to Zhcted for a bit.
[gasps]
[ELEN] There's a good
friend of mine,
a war maiden, in fact,
that I'm indebted to.
Alexandra Alshavin.
But I call her
Sasha for short.
[ELEN] Legnica,
which Sasha governs,
is facing attack
from another war maiden.
And I'm obligated
to come to her defense.
[TIGRE] Obligated?
We swore an oath
to protect each other,
so whenever
either of us is in danger,
[ELEN] the other one
will drop everything,
no matter what,
and come running.
Sasha suffers from
a serious illness.
[ELEN] When I visited her
this past summer,
she could barely even
walk on her own.
And yet, through it all,
her dragon gear
is always by her side.
[ELEN]
And so... And so... I...
[TIGRE] I get it.
[ELEN gasps]
And while you're away,
I'll do whatever I can
to help here.
[ELEN] Thank you.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
just as he had promised,
Roland made his way to
Brune's royal capital of Nice.
[ROLAND] I am Roland
of the Order of Navarre.
I have an urgent matter
to discuss with His Majesty
It's imperative
that I see him right away.
[CHAMBERLAIN 8A]
Please wait in here.
[door shuts, locks]
[ROLAND grunts]
[GANELON] Ah, Roland.
Ganelon? What's this about?
[GANELON] You dare to
show your face in the capital
after failing to
vanquish the traitor?
Such disgrace is
to be roundly punished,
not rewarded by
an audience with the king.
[gasps]
[GANELON] Thousands of bees
with venom strong enough
to kill even a lion
are now filling the room.
You're trapped in
a prison of bees, Roland.
A hellish way to die.
Farewell to you, mightiest
knight in all the land.
[FARON] Roland.
You shall be a knight
among knights.
[ROLAND] Your Majesty.
We'll return soon.
Goodbye for now, Lord Tigre.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
Thanks for everything.
You take care.
Elen will back very soon.
It's nothing to worry about.
[clanging]
Sending a woman off
with a smile.
Ah, just one of the perks
of being a man.
[TIGRE chuckles softly]
Why'd you decide
to stay behind?
[RYURIK] Winters in Brune...
They're a lot milder than the
winters back home, Lord Tigre.
Though with my head exposed
to the elements now,
a good chill
may come about easier.
[TIGRE] Got it.
Lady Eleonora left a thousand
Zhcted soldiers behind.
I sincerely hope
our duty shall far exceed
your expectations, My Lord.
We're all quite fond of you.
[MASHAS] Roland is dead.
[gasps]
[MASHAS] Executed.
What the hell?
Did you even stop to think?
Sorry, what is this about?
Roland, of course!
Why did you kill him?
Oh.
[GANELON]
Yes, that's Roland for you.
He died standing on his feet.
Magnificent, even in death.
And what about
the western border?
Sachstein and Ahsvarre will
surely take advantage of this!
Well not much we can do about
him being dead now, is there?
[GANELON] The western defense
is secure for the time being.
A much more pressing concern
is our southern border.
The army of Muozinel is
rapidly closing in on us
both by land and by sea.
So the question should be,
how safe is your territory?
[THENARDIER] Why, you...
[NARRATOR] The kingdom of
Muozinel is the only
neighboring nation with
a system of slavery in place.
They invade other lands
without provocation,
slaughtering and
plundering at will.
There is no reason
in their choice of targets
and the kingdom of Brune
has always been at a loss
for how to deal with them.
[grunts]
[screams]
[commotion]
[NARRATOR] The invading horde
is twenty thousand strong.
Thenardier's response is to
divide his forces in two.
Leading a contingent
of seven thousand,
he plans to concede
the southern province
of Agnes and its lands,
and lure the invading army
deeper into the country,
where he can defeat them
from a superior position.
[NARRATOR] His remaining
thirteen thousand are sent
to Nice, ostensibly to
protect the capital,
but also to contain
the actions of Ganelon,
who is marshaling troops
in the north.
[THENARDIER]
With Ganelon in check
and the slavers exhausting
themselves in the south,
let's see how the boy
from Alsace will react.
[TIGRE]
Twenty thousand invaders.
What can I do?
Stay here and
reinforce our defenses?
But then...
[ROLAND] I leave Durandal
in your charge.
Consider this my recognition
of your cause as a just one.
My cause is just.
[TITTA]
Lord Tigre, may I come in?
[TIGRE] Titta? What are you
doing here at this hour?
It's morning already.
I take it you never
went to bed last night?
Guess not.
It's delicious, as always.
You're the commanding
officer here now, Lord Tigre.
That means you really
need to be getting more rest.
Well. Least my wounds healed.
Thanks to you, of course.
[gasps]
Titta.
Yes?
I'm going off
on a smaller campaign.
You stay here
with Bertrand, okay?
Uh!
But you'll be...
coming back safe, right?
[TIGRE] I promise.
Do we have any hope
of winning this one?
I'm not sure.
Come on, if you can't
say there's at least
a chance of success,
then how am I supposed to
motivate the rank and file?
We're two thousand.
They're twenty.
If I said we had a shot
at winning, who'd believe me?
Well in my experience,
people will believe
what they want to believe.
So just make us want to.
Huh.
First off...
I'll take a
smaller group of men.
We'll head to Agnes.
They're being slaughtered.
If we don't protect them,
then who will?
Understood. But speaking
of protection,
shouldn't we strengthen
Territoire's defenses, too?
It's a matter of triage.
When twenty thousand
men attack,
would they be able to hold?
It might buy us some time.
At least until
the knights sent by
other noblemen can get there.
Might be enough
to dissuade the enemy
[AUGRE] from attacking
Territoire at all.
But the worst case
is also possible.
You mean no
reinforcements come, right?
I suppose we are
considered traitors
to the throne right now.
No one could fault them
if they chose to
stay out of it
and let us die.
As such, I need to ask
a favor of you both.
[NARRATOR] Turning from
a domestic conflict
between noblemen, Tigre leads
seventeen hundred men
toward the southeast border
to stop a foreign invasion
and prevent
a national crisis.
Lord Tigre. I beg.
[TITTA] Please be safe.
It's not enough
to just drive them away.
We must free those people.
[TIGRE]
Can I use this bow to do it?
No. I still haven't mastered
its mysterious power yet.
Shall we take aim?
[TIGRE] Not till tomorrow.
We're just here to scout.
Yes, of course.
So what do you think
of Viscount Augre's son?
If I may ask.
Oh, Gerard?
Good with numbers.
He's very precise.
[TIGRE] In fact, it's thanks
to him that I was able to
focus on fighting during
the battle against Roland.
There's just something
about him I don't like.
It's as though he's
looking down on everyone.
Now, now,
let's try to play nice.
[TIGRE] What's that?
[gasps]
[GIRL] Uh!
You all right?
[TIGRE]
No need to be afraid.
I'm Tigrevurmud Vorn.
From Brune.
Tigre... vurmud.
[TIGRE] Hey, Ryurik!
Come give me a hand!
[GERARD] Each bowman is
allotted fifty-six arrows.
I made sure that twelve
stones were distributed
to each cavalryman
and that the foot soldiers
received five apiece.
However,
for a large-scale battle,
those won't last long.
We need more.
And there's another problem.
Muozinel has captured and
enslaved many of our people.
If they use them
as human shields,
we won't be able to attack.
Understood.
The sun will be up soon.
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F] General,
enemy forces have arrived.
They appear to be
a Brunish army.
How many?
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F] Between
a hundred and two hundred.
All cavalrymen.
They're keeping their distance
while attacking our left flank
with stones and arrows.
Send three thousand
infantrymen to crush them.
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F]
But sir, isn't three thousand
a little excessive?
Surely five hundred
would be more than enough.
They're merely a decoy.
Hit their main formation.
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F]
Yes, sir.
If that's their decoy,
the main force
should be two thousand.
[NARRATOR] Under orders from
their supreme commander, Kasim,
three thousand enemy soldiers,
a group of
bowmen and spearmen,
chase after the
two hundred Brunish troops.
[NARRATOR] Passing through
a narrow bottleneck,
they come to a dead end.
There, the lead
Muozinellan soldiers
are stunned by what they see.
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8G]
Their main battalion?
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8H]
We can't stop that many
mounted soldiers!
[TIGRE] Forward attack!
[BRUNE SOLDIERS yelling]
[MUOZINEL COMMANDER 8A]
Retreat! Fall back!
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8H]
Sir, we can't!
We'll be pinned against
our own rear guard!
I'd say our first battle
went surprisingly well.
Gather up any weapons
we can still use!
[NARRATOR] Tigre devised
strategy after strategy,
concentrating his efforts
on tripping up the enemy army
and whittling away
at their numbers.
After repeated sneak-attacks,
the twenty thousand
were cut down
to nineteen thousand
and soon, eighteen thousand.
As for Kasim's attempts
to counter Tigre...
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8I]
You cowards of Brune,
slithering around
like slimy little worms,
hiding safely
behind your rocks!
We aren't going to put up
with your sneaky tricks
and games forever!
If you choose
to conceal yourselves,
this is what happens!
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8I]
Kill them!
[arrows fire]
[BRUNE CITIZENS scream]
Forward march.
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F]
Forward march!
[NARRATOR] That day,
the Muozinellan army
sent out an advance squad
of three thousand,
with the main unit
positioned behind.
Kasim had decided that
the enemy were few in number
and there was no way
that they could fight head-on.
However,
the Silver Meteor Storm
now stood before them
with six hundred soldiers.
Is that all? I thought they
might finally show themselves.
Where's their commander?
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F]
Perhaps it's that young man
in the center who's stepping
out to the forefront?
Never.
Brunishmen despise archery.
There's no way they'd make
a bowman their captain.
Is this another decoy?
Listen up, you barbarians!
You revolting monsters!
[TIGRE] For the way you
slaughter and enslave
the innocent,
you deserve to die!
So make your peace now,
before it's too late!
Get within firing range
and shoot him.
[distant yelling]
[MUOZINEL SOLDIERS] Huh?
Yet another ambush?
Same old tricks.
Huh?
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8N]
The Zhcted army?
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8O]
It can't be!
Attack now!
Everybody charge!
[yelling]
Huh. They may have
caught us off guard,
but it looks like there are
only two thousand of them.
Their parlor tricks
won't be enough
to defeat our
advanced squad. Uh!
Much too eager.
He's over three hundred
alsins away.
It'll never--
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8F]
Lord Kasim!
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8P]
Lord Kasim's been shot!
[MUOZINEL SOLDIER 8Q]
How? From where!
Behold! Our leader,
Count Tigrevurmud Vorn,
has single-handedly
taken out their general!
[BRUNE SOLDIERS holler]
[MUOZINEL SOLDIERS yell]
All units follow them!
Hunt down and kill
every last one!
Well, that was a lot
closer than I imagined.
All thanks to
their recklessness.
That's why he put his
main force out in front of him.
I bet he never considered that,
despite their
contempt for bows.
Somewhere in the Brunish army,
there could possibly be
an archer with enough skill
to hit a target
three hundred alsins away.
[TIGRE chuckles]
[GERARD] They're fleeing
back to Muozinel.
Ryurik, can you
handle the pursuit?
[RYURIK] Yes, sir.
[murmurs]
[MAN 8B] Why didn't you
get here sooner?
Why? Tell me why
you didn't show yourselves
this morning when
I'm sure you could have!
You must've been nearby.
If you'd only come out then,
well then I wouldn't have
had to lose her!
But you didn't.
[GERARD gasps]
That's not our--
I'm sorry.
[MAN 8B gasps]
[YOUNG GIRL 8B] Excuse me.
[YOUNG GIRL 8B] Thank you
so much for saving us.
And... also...
For avenging my father
who was killed this morning.
I'm sorry, but I... well...
I don't think what that man
said before was wrong.
But still... Even so, I wanted
to give you my sincere thanks.
[TIGRE] No, it is I
who should be thanking you.
[YOUNG GIRL 8B gasps, chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
During this battle,
the Muozinellan army lost
over three thousand men.
Including casualties
from the day before,
the dead topped five thousand.
All told, a quarter of the army
had fallen in the land of Agnes.
[GERARD] After that battle,
we still have
fifteen hundred
and three men alive.
That includes four hundred
sixty-two wounded.
Some more gravely than others.
But considering our situation,
it's a miraculous outcome.
What about the
civilians we rescued?
We'll send them to Territoire
and hope defenses hold.
There's no other way.
[RYURIK] Lord Tigrevurmud.
A word?
Just an advance party?
[RYURIK]
The Muozinellans we captured
all said the same thing.
That they were only
the first wave.
[TIGRE] If those were scouts,
what about the main force?
Their number?
[RYURIK] Thirty thousand.
So many.
If they join the soldiers who
managed to get away from us,
then in a matter of
a few days,
forty thousand
will be at our door.
These non-stop battles...
they're wearing out the men.
And we still have to
move those civilians.
I thought I prepared
for the worst.
Even so, we're still not
half as far as we should be.
There's not much we can do
about falling behind.
[SILVER METEOR SOLDIER 8C]
Another Muozinellan unit
is heading this way.
There are three,
maybe four thousand soldiers.
I guess they want to
make their shot count.
Take over here.
Be careful!
[TIGRE] At least we've got
some good archers with us.
[gasps]
We can't even slow
them down... at this rate.
[horse neighs]
[TIGRE]
They brought reinforcements?
No. I know those flags.
[TIGRE] They're from Olmütz!
That's the Snow Princess
of the Frozen Ripple!
Ludmila Lourie!
It's been too long.
Did you miss me,
Count Tigrevurmud Vorn?
[LIM] The best thing
I can do to protect my lady
is to win this battle
as quickly as possible.
Episode Nine: "Thunder Swirl
and Luminous Flame."
Please watch.