[ELEN] You seem like
you're recovering well
from the snakebite.
[LIM] Indeed.
It's thanks to everyone's
quick thinking.
Of course.
Ludmila's help getting rid
of the assassins
is rather confusing, though.
As for Tigre...
Seeing him spring
into action like that
and suck out the poison
to save you was inspirational.
Yeah, I guess.
I feel bad that instead
of immediately helping,
I just stood there,
stunned like a statue.
I'm sorry...
Don't be sorry, my lady.
Well, since he
saved your life,
I've decided to give
Tigre a reward.
[TIGRE gasps]
Uhhh... Um, can...
you please cover yourself?
For modesty's sake?
Do you feel the need
to be modest
when a dog or a cat
sees you naked?
And judging by your
rather flaccid demeanor,
I'm assuming you're not here
to ravage me, either.
It was an accident.
It's my fault for not
thinking that someone else
might already be
using this bath.
Are you sure there's nothing
else you want to say?
Um... I'm sorry and
I won't do it again.
[TIGRE grunts]
So, how was it?
Your bath?
Oh, don't tell me
you set that up!
Huh? Set what up?
[LIM sighs]
[ELEN gasps]
[ELEN] What's wrong?
Does Lady Ludmila of
the proud House of Lourie
not believe in eating wheat
gruel from street vendors?
Of course I don't!
I have no appetite for it.
And the whole scene is
beneath a War Maiden's digni--
[MILA'S stomach growling]
Oh, really?
[ELEN] Ooh! This looks tasty!
[ELEN squeals, giggles]
--She's such a child...
--[ELEN] Better than I thought!
--[MILA'S stomach growling]
--[ELEN] I'm not exaggerating!
Oh, You're really
missing out, Mila.
Would you like a
serving, Lady Ludmila?
[MILA] Hmph!
I'm trying to apologize
again for earlier.
With that?
Well, I'll accept
the gesture, at least...
I'm pretty sure who was to
blame for that mix-up anyway.
So...
You know, it's not terrible!
See? I thought you'd like it.
Tigre! What're you doing?!
I could ask the
same thing of you!
I don't like you giving
that shriveled blueberry
of a war maiden
any special attention!
Shut up and kiss her!
Just kiss her, you fool!
[CROWD murmuring]
[MILA sighs]
Count Tigrevurmud Vorn...
Huh...?
You're a good-hearted man.
It's too bad that's all you are.
Like a dog, forever at
Eleonora's command.
I've lost interest in you.
That's your big
assessment of him?
That's a laugh.
[ELEN] Let me translate
what you're really saying:
"I'm a teeny little war maiden
who can't see all the things
Lord Tigre's actually good for."
How sad.
[MILA] You're pathetic.
Listen... When you get
back to Leitmeritz,
the first thing you do is
strengthen the border patrol.
You really think
the Lady would attack?
[NARRATOR]
Just as Ellen predicted,
Lady Ludmila immediately
began massing her army
on the border of Leitmeritz.
With this mobilization,
Elen found herself at a
strategic disadvantage,
sandwiched between the
forces of Duke Thenardier
and a fellow war maiden.
Such was Thenardier's hope
that the mere presence
of Ludmila's army
would hamstring Elen's movements
and thus keep
her forces in check.
[ELEN] Hmm...
Unlike his dimwit son, Zion,
Duke Felix Thenardier
is a competent tactician.
[TIGRE] Are you going
to fight Ludmila?
I think that's exactly
what she wants me to do.
Interesting.
On her own, Lady Ludmila
has little to gain
from waging war against
another war maiden.
[ELEN] But these moves allow her
to strengthen the alliance
between Thenardier and her
principality of Olmütz.
Tigre, you decide what's next.
What, me?
You can take the future
into your own hands
and strike against Ludmila...
Or send troops to Alsace
and prepare a defense
against Thenardier and Ganelon.
I'm leaving it to you.
Let's strike.
I have to take an
active role in this fight.
As you say.
But we need to make sure we
protect Viscount Augre, too,
now that we're allies.
And let's send an envoy
to Ludmila first.
Right.
[NARRATOR]
Unfortunately for Tigre,
Ludmila promptly rejected
the envoy he sent.
The forces from
Lightmeritz now advance,
while the army from Olmütz
braces itself for battle.
[MILA] Scouts report Lady
Eleonora is heading this way.
Into defeat at my own hands.
My lady,
are you sure you want to
battle the Wind Princess?
An understanding between
the House of Lourie
and the House of Thenardier has
persisted for over eighty years!
I will not let it
fall apart on my watch.
Like my Lavias here,
I also carry an ancient pride.
Eleonora does not.
[NARRATOR] The Tatra Mountains
stand to the East,
overlooking the
frozen Vloklin Plains.
Here, amid the
cold and falling snow,
the first round of battle began
between the two war maidens.
[horns sounding]
[LEITMERITZ SOLDIERS yelling]
[OLMÜTZ SOLDIERS yelling]
[LEITMERITZ CHIEF CAVALRYMAN A]
Nice shot, my lord!
These guys don't go down easy.
[NARRATOR] Battlefield momentum
ebbed and flowed for hours,
before day one ultimately
ended in stalemate,
and the two armies withdrew
to lick their wounds.
[ELEN] So, what do you
think of Ludmila's men?
It doesn't matter
how hard you hit them.
They get right back up.
[ELEN] I agree.
Mila has always been
strong on defense.
The best of all the war maidens.
Which is doubly funny
because she can be
so damn aggressive in person!
Thankfully,
I don't recall seeing her
fighting in the front lines
all that much today.
Well, I'd like to
keep it that way.
When all's said and done,
she can't beat me
in a pitched battle.
In the morning, I'll stand
at the head of our army,
and then I will
crush her myself.
Lady Eleonora,
what is your current record
in one-on-one combat
against the Lady from Olmütz?
I'm up two to one!
[LIM] Yes, but I've
heard Ludmila say
she has the exact
same record against you.
How can that be?
As near as I can tell,
one of their duels was a draw...
But ever since,
both of them have claimed it
as one of their wins
against the other.
[TIGRE] You two just
don't get along, do you?
Olmütz and Leitmeritz
not getting along
might as well be
an ancient tradition.
How do you mean?
War maidens from
the House of Lourie,
like Mila's mother
and grandmother,
they're always hostile.
Mother and grandmother?
Are war maidens dynastic?
Not quite.
We're chosen by a
Dragon Gear weapon.
Well, I'll give you the rest
of the history lesson later.
In the present,
we've got a battle to win.
[LIM] It's like the
Olmütz Army was never even here!
I believe they've withdrawn
into the Tatra Mountains.
She tricked us!
Wait, you think this was a ploy?
That Ludmila was planning
this move from the beginning?
She wasn't trying to destroy us
during yesterday's battle.
She was just feeling us out!
[NARRATOR] High atop
the Tatra Mountains
is a citadel with
only one way in...
Any attacking force will
quickly find itself surrounded
by well-entrenched
defensive fortifications.
Looks like she
wants us to lay siege.
The way's frozen over.
She did it with her Lavias,
to deny us a good position.
It's more effective
than any moat.
I've heard my ancestors also
had considerable difficulty
with this place.
Oh, well.
I won't let that stop me!
[LEITMERITZ SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARRATOR] The Leitmeritz Army
surged forward to the Citadel,
but the Olmütz forces
gave no ground.
Elen's men had no choice
but to fall back.
Once more,
the day ended in stalemate.
[LIM] How many times
must I say this?!
It's a bad idea!
The way this
offensive is going,
the battle will never end!
And if her soldiers don't
kill my men, the cold will!
So I'll use Arifal's power
to fly behind their camp,
and wipe out
Ludmila's whole rotten army!
Lord Tigre, please try
to talk her out of this!
Her plan's too reckless!
Tigre!
Who's prisoner-of-war are you?
I'm yours, my Lady.
That's exactly right!
Which means you should
always trust my instincts,
obey my orders, and pray
for my safety in battle!
You understand?
[TIGRE] Listen...
I hold you in very high regard!
I know I've asked you a lot by
deciding to meet her in battle.
My people are in your debt.
So the last thing I'd want...
...is for you to go
on a suicide mission.
[ELEN] Oh, really?
That's right.
Are you sure, Tigre?
You really, truly care
that much about me?
Yes, I really do.
I'm your favorite?
What's that?
What were you just
thinking about?
My homeland.
[ELEN gasps]
[ELEN giggles]
[ELEN] Your heart really does
belong to that little province,
doesn't it? Well, that's okay.
Because after all, both you
and Alsace now belong to me.
If you want to get technical.
By the way, if you would
have answered my question
with the name
of another woman...
Well, let's just say that Arifal
here has also been known
to separate heads
from their bodies.
So mentioning Alsace
was the best way
to stay on my
good side. Smart man.
[LIM sighs]
[TIGRE] So are you still
going through with your plan?
Give me a better one,
and I'll follow it
without complaint.
I have an idea, but...
I'll need another favor.
[TIGRE] Three days in.
[LIM] Here you go.
[TIGRE] A bear skin?
Hey, I heard a story
once about a village
where the men wore animal
skins when they hunted.
Just give it a try.
It might even save your life
[TIGRE grunts]
[TIGRE] Hey! It's heavy...
[LIM] Hmm...
Looks good.
[TIGRE] Huh?
I didn't say anything.
Are you sure he'll be okay
wearing just that thing?
Oh, I'll be fine...
And I promise,
I will find another path
for us to that citadel.
[TIGRE] I still have water...
But I need to find food.
...What?
[MILA] I take it
that's your arrow?
Lady... Aren't you cold
dressed like that?
I'm well adapted to this
climate; I think I'll be fine.
You walked a long way to
get to this spot, didn't you?
How many paces away
did you shoot this animal?
There's no way you're
that good of a shot...
Don't lie to me, commoner.
[MILA gasps]
I'm sorry, sir...
I guess I shouldn't have doubted
that you're skilled with a bow.
[TIGRE] She can
actually be quite nice.
[MILA] You can
take that off now.
We're inside where it's warm.
As long as you're
in my presence,
the biting cold and snow
shouldn't be a problem for you.
[TIGRE] According to
the laws of my village.
I'm not to remove this suit
while on the hunt
in the mountains.
Well then,
that's too bad.
Tell me your name.
[TIGRE] It's Urs.
Are you a war maiden, my lady?
[MILA] Yes, I am...
And you don't seem that
surprised by it, either.
Well, I don't mind...
Thanks to your great skill
with the bow and arrow,
I'll look past
your blunt manners.
I have an idea...
You should come and serve
in my court, Urs...
Like I was getting at,
a man with your talent is rare.
You could make a good living.
I came to the Tatra Mountains
from a distant land.
I won't turn my back on my home
for any amount of riches.
I see... That's too bad.
[TIGRE] Besides, aren't you
worried I might be a spy?
[MILA] That's a weird thing
for you to bring up now...
You can relax...
I'd believe a great
bow hunter like yourself
could make it this far.
But a common soldier or spy
doesn't have a chance.
[MILA] I know!
[MILA] Go on. Try it!
[TIGRE] It's... good!
[MILA giggles]
Glad you like it!
Tea's the best, isn't it?
Warms the body and the soul.
[TIGRE] She's smiling?
I didn't know she was
capable of that!
[MILA] What's the matter, Urs?
Tell me.
[TIGRE] It's nothing.
Now tell me, why's a
war maiden out alone up here?
[MILA] Looking for fun.
It sounds... weird to say
that out loud.
[TIGRE] If there's
something you wanna say,
I'm a very good listener.
[TIGRE] Whatever you need
to get off your chest.
It's like the old fable
about the frustrated man
who yells into a tree hollow.
[MILA] You know, I never
expected to meet a bear up here,
let alone one as nice as you.
When I was chosen
to be a war maiden,
I thought I was ready
to shoulder all
of its responsibilities.
But... For the good
of my country,
that means being bound by
old ties to people I hate.
So in the name
of tradition,
I told myself I had to
bury my true feelings.
And I thought that I was right.
But now I'm not so sure.
[MILA] Goodbye
and safe hunting, Urs!
I won't forget you!
And if you're ever feel
like visiting me,
you're welcome any time
at the Palace in Olmütz!
[TIGRE] This isn't good...
Once the sun goes down...
[TIGRE] ...I won't be able to
follow her tracks anymore.
I've found it...
The alternate route
to the Citadel.
All right, men! Almost there!
Her guard detail
in the rear is light...
If we can just get in there,
even a hundred of us...
[ELEN] This is more
than I expected.
Maybe she grew cautious
after meeting a stranger
in a bear suit.
So what are we
supposed to do?
Turn back?
No. If we give up now,
we're just doing exactly
what the enemy wants.
We have to assume that
while we're up here,
Thenardier may be
closing in on Alsace.
I'm taking down
this citadel tonight!
Elen, wait!
Dragon, who brings victory,
be with us this night!
Ley... Ad Mos!
[ELEN gasps]
Elen!
[ELEN grunts]
Dammit, Tigre!
You just ruined my chance
to hit them again!
Come on!
They were about to
turn you into a pincushion!
[ELEN gasps]
There's no other way in!
Or have you forgotten that?!
It's no use. Now they
know we're here.
[ELEN] We have to keep trying!
There's no time!
Not for you, or for Alsace!
Let me think...
There's has to be a move left.
Think!
[TIGRE gasps]
[TIGRE] Arifal!
[ELEN] What?
[TIGRE] Please, Arifal...
Lend me your strength.
I know that Elen is the only
master to whom you answer...
There is no physical or
spiritual connection between us.
But just this once,
lend me your strength!
Two-timer...
All right, here we go.
Follow me!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Stay behind her, men!
Don't fall back!
[MILA] They've broken
through the rear gate?!
Dammit, Eleonora!
[ELEN yells]
[TIGRE yells]
[NARRATOR] The mighty citadel at
the top of the Tatra Mountains
has been breached.
The next round in the battle
between war maidens begins!
[ELEN] I need to use my
Dragon Art. But can I?
[ELEN] Episode 6,
"The Black Knight."
Watch carefully.