[BLACK BOW] Good for you, Tigre.
It seems you've finally mastered
the power of the Black Bow.
And you did it all by yourself.
Without anyone's help.
You shot clear through that
bedrock that entombed you.
Bertrand...
Bertrand.
[TIGRE] I...
[TITTA gasps]
Hate to intrude.
I know you're sad,
so I'll get to it.
What do you want to do now?
[TIGRE] Ask me in the morning.
I worry the longer you take.
The less thought you'll
actually put into your plan.
It'll be perfunctory.
Something you come up with
just to meet a deadline.
Listen, it's possible for
you to end this whole war,
right here, tonight.
Offer the right conditions
and perhaps we can
bargain with Thenardier.
Alsace will be secure.
What about your goals
in this war?
[ELEN] You should know
the answer to that by now.
I'll get what I want.
[TITTA whimpers]
Yes. That's right.
Whatever you decide
to do with Thenardier,
however we choose to act,
what matters to me is
fighting battles I can
take pride in. That is all.
That's what drives you
through all this? Your pride?
[ELEN] Correct.
It's the pride
I have as a warrior.
It's something
I always carry with me.
There was a time when
I was a mercenary.
I had no land to go home to.
So I wandered the earth,
from one battle to the next.
I assumed all my friends
would die eventually.
I had nothing else
to hold on to.
That's why it was so important
to keep my pride.
The one constant
that made me who I am.
Your pride.
[TIGRE] Well, you may have your
pride, I've still got my mettle!
It's what I inherited
from my father
and the long line of Vorns
before him. That's why I fight!
Mettle.
[TIGRE] That is my constant.
Like your pride, mettle is
what makes me who I am.
[TITTA whimpers]
[TIGRE] Titta.
[TITTA gasps]
You're so strong.
I know I scared you.
I'm sorry.
[TITTA whimpers]
Oh, Lord Tigre!
[TITTA sobs]
Once this war's over for good,
we'll go back home to Alsace
and have a proper funeral.
[sobbing continues]
Okay?
We'll honor Bertrand right.
[TITTA] Yes... Okay...
Old Bertrand. He said
he used to worry
I loved Alsace so much
I'd ignore the greater world.
But in the very end he was
relieved that's not true.
Well on the subject
of the greater world,
I think it's time you
learned the other reason
I've been helping
you in your Brunish War.
Huh?
[ELEN] And it's not a
sentimental reason.
It's practical. Political.
All right, I'm listening.
Why did Muozinel attack the
Agnes region of Brune
in the South? Why did they
try to conquer a port town?
So that... they could control
some routes of trade?
The bigger picture.
You see it now?
The ties that can bind us,
separate from any war.
Binding ties? Trade routes?
[TIGRE gasps]
The Vozh mountains.
If we could build a trade route
through the range
connecting Alsace
with Leitmeritz,
then Leitmeritz would be--
[ELEN] Mm-hmm.
There's much more to war
than fleeting conquests
of land and treasure.
By opening new roads, and
exchanging goods and culture,
it can grow your
land's wealth, inexorably.
And secure its prosperity.
But could Alsace?
It could change; it's true.
For the better or for the worse.
But that depends on how capable
the person governing it is.
And whether he takes
the broad view
of what's happening around him.
You're talking again
about the "big picture."
[TIGRE gasps]
How you doing?
[RYURIK laughs nervously]
How long have you
been standing there?
This-This dandy of a Brunishman
couldn't concentrate
on his work, so he kept me
from doing my own!
Well, that's only because this
bald Zhcted subject
is so fidgety I can't
focus on my own.
Hey!
Tigre. We've all been
waiting for you.
So, think you're ready now?
[TIGRE] I appreciate
your support, everyone.
[BADOUIN] Prime Minister
of Brune, Pierre Badouin.
Humbly at your service.
I am relieved to find
you safe, Princess Regin.
His Majesty informed me of
everything that's happened.
Glad to hear it.
Well, Prime Minister.
We meet at last.
[BADOUIN laughs]
When you were a boy,
you accompanied your father
on a visit to the palace.
It has been far too long since
we last met, Lord Tigrevurmud.
So, what brings you
here, Badouin?
At long last, King Faron
has regained his wits.
[gasping]
We've discovered that he'd
been repeatedly poisoned
by Duke Ganelon.
[REGIN gasps]
[MASHAS] What?
[BADOUIN] Lord Tigrevurmud.
Would you be so kind as to
tell me your intentions?
Your plans for this war,
and for its aftermath.
I will beat Thenardier's army.
And kill the duke.
[BADOUIN] Then will you
try to conquer Brune?
No, I won't.
Once Alsace is secure,
I will return to Zhcted
as Eleonora's prisoner.
Hey! Hold on!
I don't think you need to use
terms like "prisoner" anymore.
That's a good point.
To be more respectful,
I'll accept you as a
"foreign guest of honor."
[ELEN growls]
[ELEN] Cram it,
rotten blueberry!
[MILA] No, you cram it!
My lord, are you sure you want
to remain a ward of Zhcted
just to protect Alsace?
[TIGRE] I am.
But, look, there's more
to this deal
than just me going over there.
If it can lead to lasting peace
and security for Alsace,
I'll be okay with Zhcted
annexing my homeland,
like I originally agreed.
[MASHAS] Well then,
Prime Minister.
What do you think we should do?
Take Her Highness to the royal
capital in Nice, and hurry.
[BOTH gasp]
[BADOUIN] I fear His Majesty
doesn't have much time left.
[REGIN gasps]
But knowing Duke Thenardier,
He'll try to block us from
entering the capital, so...
The final showdown.
[NARRATOR]
Tigre's assumption is correct,
and the two armies clash
on the wilds of Mereville.
[MASHAS] Don't worry,
Your Highness.
[REGIN gasps]
Our knights hold
the right flank.
While Ryurik and our
Zhcted allies are in control
of the left. And the center is--
No. It's not that.
I'm wondering if it's right
that I'm the commander
for this battle.
Lord Tigre would be much better.
Princess. This battle is to win
you entrance to the capital.
To secure your claim,
you must command.
Yes.
So far, it looks quite clear
that we have the
upper hand. However...
[MASHAS] The movements
of Thenardier's army
are clumsy today.
At first, I thought
it might be a trap;
most likely their field
commander's death
at the Holy Grotto is affecting
their performance and morale.
In that case. Duke Thenardier
should be leading
the charge himself out
there on the battlefield.
Well, clearly he's not!
And the result of
that absence is obvious.
But what if he's--
You've come.
[SOLDIERS yell]
[SOLDIER grunts, yells]
Had I just marched
on the capital,
I might have won
this stupid war.
I could have barricaded
myself in the castle,
traded land for time,
refit my men.
But the window for that
strategy has closed.
Why did you do it?
What made you decide
to attack Alsace?
Because if I controlled Alsace,
I could prevent Zhcted
from interfering in Brune.
And that buffer would be assured
by turning Alsace
into a wasteland. Torching
the land. Killing its people.
That's why you did this?!
With good cause!
The fact is, you're the one who
invited in the Zhcted army.
And if you hadn't, that
miserable troll Ganelon
surely would have
done so later.
After all, he and Zhcted
have a long history together.
But then, so do I.
[MILA gasps]
[TIGRE] I can't forgive you
for the suffering
you've caused Alsace,
let alone Brune!
Nor can I ever forgive you
for killing my son Zion
at the Molsheim Plains.
[BLACK BOW] You have mastered
the power I've given you,
Count Vorn.
But if you desire it,
you could have so much more.
More power!
[ELEN] Hey.
[TIGRE grunts]
[MILA gasps]
I won't tell you it's wrong
to want vengeance,
but don't let hate consume you.
[TIGRE gasps]
[ELEN] It's the last thing
to use as a weapon.
[BERTRAND] Laddy! Laddy!
He's here for
vengeance, too. Right?
[TIGRE] I'll be back.
[THENARDIER growls]
[MILA gasps]
[THENARDIER] You're dueling me
with but a single arrow?
One shot is all I need.
Any more would weaken my mettle.
Your funeral.
Yah!
[TIGRE] Guide my arrow,
Eris, Goddess of Wind.
[TIGRE gasps]
[THENARDIER]
Losing your nerve, boy?!
Die, Vorn!
[ELEN gasps]
[THENARDIER yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[THENARDIER groans]
[THENARDIER] Vorn... How...?
The... wind...
Brune... Brune...
[THENARDIER rasps]
Was that wind you, Arifal?
It wasn't? Well, then.
Tigre defeated
Thenardier on his own.
The wind became his ally.
You're right. So it did.
[NARRATOR] And so the war
that began for Tigre
on the Dinant Plains
came to a victorious close.
[GANELON] The bow has been left
in your charge, Count Vorn.
You may go ahead
and increase your power
to any level you desire.
[VALENTINA] They're due to start
boarding in just a moment,
Duke Ganelon.
Oh! It's been a long time
since we've seen each other.
Lady Valentina Glinka Estes.
I am in your debt, my beauty.
Oh, I'm always glad to help!
You know, I forgot.
We'll be missing the
triumphant home coming.
[VALENTINA giggles]
[VALENTINA] The one for
Count Tigrevurmud Vorn.
[CROWD cheers]
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Too loud!
[MAN A] Long live Brune!
[WOMAN A] Long live Count Vorn!
[cheering continues]
[WOMAN B] I see Count Vorn!
[MAN B] Long live the Princess!
[TIGRE groans]
[REGIN giggles]
You finally look
the part, Count Vorn.
Uh! Thanks, Princess!
Sorry...
Handsome either way.
--Uh. Yeah...
--[REGIN giggles]
[TIGRE} You're pretty, too.
I mean, thanks. I'm not used
to doing stuff like this.
Ordinarily under
these circumstances
I'd be the one
sitting next to Tigre.
Right. And the
same goes for me.
Well, let her have him.
After today, Tigre will be
coming to live in Leitmeritz.
It's more like,
Tigre will be coming to live
somewhere in Zhcted.
[BOTH growls]
[ELEN] You can't let
anything go, can you?!
[MILA] What, and you can?!
[LIM sighs]
[CROWD appluading]
[TITTA giggles]
[BADOUIN] He's resting in here.
He's already receiving a guest.
An envoy from Zhcted.
[ALL] Huh?
[BADOUIN] This way.
[ELEN] Sofy?
Hi, Elen!
[REGIN gasps]
The Prime Minister.
He's brought me up to speed.
I am so sorry,
I failed you, Regin.
The Dukes took advantage
of me because I lacked
the insight needed as
both King and Father.
[REGIN] No... Don't say that...
[FARON] I was the one given the
duty to protect this kingdom,
but my absence instead
forced it entirely onto you.
Count Tigrevurmud Vorn.
What are your wishes, young man?
I do have some, Your Majesty.
[NARRATOR] Tigre suggests four
basic provisions to the King.
In essence, it is a
conventional peace treaty.
But the Brunish
province of Agnes,
abandoned during
the brief war with Muozinel,
would be ceded to Zhcted.
Faron agrees, and makes
Princess Regin a signatory.
By her signing the treaty,
it's clear to Zhcted,
as well as any potential
rebel elements in Brune,
that Faron recognizes her as the
Kingdom's next rightful ruler.
Oh, and Count Vorn.
Sire!
[FARON] There's something I'd
like to give you personally,
as thanks for all you've done.
I bestow on you the title of...
Lumiere, royal Knight
of the Moonlight.
[BADOUIN gasps]
[TIGRE] Thank you, Your Majesty!
[RYURIK] Congratulations,
Count Vorn!
[ELEN] Wow, first meteors
and now moonlight!
[GERARD] Yes, job
well done, Tigre!
Long live the Knight
of the Moonlight!
[MILA] C'mon,
show some excitement!
[TIGRE] It's bad form
in front of the King.
[NARRATOR] Several days later,
King Faron of Brune
quietly takes his last breath
and dies peacefully.
[TITTA giggles]
Hey! Stop! Lunie,
you'll make me drop it!
[RYURIK] Lady Titta!
Do you know where
Lord Tigre's run off to?
He's hunting.
It's spring, y'know!
[TITTA giggles]
[ELEN] How's the Vosyes
trade route coming?
[LIM] Brunish engineers
have recently arrived
and begun preparing. Once
the first thaw comes,
they'll start moving earth.
So it sounds like dear Regin
is keeping up her end
of the treaty. That's good.
My lady, recall that Alsace is
under the joint control
of both you and Regin.
Officially, this agreement was
not made between two countries,
but between a princess and a
province. So that means--
[ELEN] I get it.
If she weren't such
an honorable person
we might have had a problem.
[ELEN] We've all got
our eyes on you, now.
[ELEN] The question is,
where are your eyes looking?
[BADOUIN]
Knight of the Moonlight.
Some of the men
who receive that title
have gone onto become king.
Don't tell me he could--
[ELEN] I know one thing for
sure, Tigre: I'm so glad we met.
[TIGRE grunts]