Flat-chested dwarf!
Illiterate boor!
[SASHA]
That's enough, you two!
What are you doing?
[SASHA] Hmm?
[BOTH] Um, it's because
she came at me!
It's her fault!
Uh! Not you!
If you want to fight...
then I guess I'll just
have to fight too.
[BOTH gasp]
To save time, you can
both come at me at once.
If either of your blades
manages to draw blood,
I'll give you a prize.
[SASHA] Which is...
I know! The two of you
get to order me
around for a day!
If you don't want to fight me,
you can just make up.
[BOTH grunt]
[weapons clanging]
[birds chirp]
[ELEN, MILA groans]
[gasps]
Want some more?
[BOTH] Mm-mmm.
[SASHA] You should only
turn your dragon gear
on another person
when there's a good reason.
And a feud like this isn't one.
Now, shake hands and make up.
Come on...
[bird caws]
Hello! I really appreciate
you making the journey here!
That's our agreement!
[SASHA]
And these little fellas,
well they're even happier
than I am to see you.
So... Let's start off
with the most important stuff.
The woman who's marched
an army into your land
without any reason or warning!
Elizaveta Fomina...
Flash Princess
of the Thunder Swirl.
[growls]
What could possibly
motivate her to do this?
[SASHA] I'll explain.
But I need you to stay calm.
[gasps]
It was the middle
of last summer.
Elizaveta and I
were campaigning together,
fighting a pirate band
that was raiding the coast.
And just as we finished up,
she accused me
of not being fair.
According to her,
my soldiers funneled
the pirates toward her lines,
so they had to
bear the full brunt.
[ELEN]
Is there any truth to that?
I read the reports,
but I can't say either way.
I haven't been able
to talk to her,
because she abruptly stopped
writing me in the fall.
And that's when Lady Elizaveta
mobilized her men against you?
She was just looking for
any excuse to invade!
Being ill, you'd think
these little ones
would find me unworthy
of being a war maiden
and choose someone else...
[SASHA] Then I wouldn't
have to turn to you now,
or even be in
this situation at all.
But, they don't agree.
[ELEN] Well, I think
it's a beautiful thing!
War maidens are chosen
by their Dragon Gear...
and because of this,
my problem is now yours.
Stop worrying about it, Sasha!
I'm happy to be here;
it's no problem.
I'll drive that scheming
Elizaveta out of Legnica!
And let you get back
to recuperating!
[SASHA] That reminds me...
From what I hear,
you've been on some interesting
military adventures lately.
In one of Sofy's letters,
she mentioned something
about you even going to Brune?
[ELEN] Yes. There's a young
count in all kinds of trouble.
I couldn't abandon him
to the dukes there,
so I'm lending him a hand.
Seems like it's more you
who's been lent a hand by him.
Oh, please, Lim; don't act
like you're above it all.
I have vivid memories
of him saving your life
with his mouth
right on your breast...
Uh!
Sounds like you've both really
taken to this Brunish noble.
He's a fascinating fellow.
If you get to talk to him,
you'll like him right away, too!
Sasha, I have to bring him
here sometime to say hello.
And I might even
let you borrow him...
[ELEN] ...for a little bit.
Well then, that all
sounds like a lot of fun.
I'll make sure I hold on
a little longer.
[LIM] Mm?
[KUREYS] A Zhcted army?
I have been hearing
through our spy network
that a minor nobleman
in Brune formed an alliance
with a Zhcted Army. Huh.
They've committed
several thousand soldiers,
but why? What does
Zhcted have to gain
from allying with
such a lesser partner?
Hmmm.
[KUREYS] Listen up!
Send an envoy to this girl!
If the war maiden
is as beautiful as
her reputation holds,
then give her my full support!
[ADVISORS] Sire...
[KUREYS] If she's
more man than woman,
tell the envoy he's welcome
to return empty-handed!
[laughs]
[MILA]
That's your first demerit.
[TIGRE] What?
Your greeting began
with you saying,
"Thank you for saving us."
It's not smart
to assume generosity.
[MILA] For all you know,
I might demand
compensation for the help.
And what should I make
of you giving me this tea
before I said a word?
I make tea for
everyone I parlay with,
even those I hate.
[MILA]
This way, if talks go badly,
I have something
to throw in their faces.
All right, Ludmila,
what are you doing here?
Why do you think I'm here?
Do you want me?
[gasps]
[MILA] I'm asking if you want
me and the four thousand men
under me to be your allies.
Of course!
[MILA] Second demerit!
I know you're hard up,
but you're coming across
too desperate and it gives
away your bad position.
And I will not enter into
an alliance with a fool.
Please help me, Ludmila!
[MILA gasps]
[TIGRE] I don't have
anything of worth
to offer you right now,
but if you can wait until
the war's over, I promise
I'll come up with something.
[MILA]
Lift up your head, Tigre.
I wonder what's
a better description.
Are you honest out of
moral conviction,
or, because you're a fool...
Either way,
you've passed the test.
So you are helping me?
[MILA] The negotiation
is only just starting.
First up, show me what
my help is worth to you...
[TIGRE] Um...
[MILA] In the battle
at the Tatra Mountains,
you guys were able to
destroy the ancient citadel's
rear gateway, right?
[MILA] The fact is,
that gate had a very unique,
and very clever design.
It got its structural strength
from three plates of iron,
with each plate having
oak planks between them.
[MILA] Even Arifal couldn't
knock down that gate.
It was you who did it.
[MILA] Did she
tell you to keep quiet?
[chuckles softly]
You know...
I once bought into the idea
that you were different--
As straight and true
with your words
as you are with your arrows,
and I want to believe
that once again...
So tell the truth.
So this is it? I expected
something more sophisticated
for the shots you make.
[TIGRE] Hey, come on, that's a
cherished family heirloom.
Don't go bad mouthing it
in front of me.
Why don't you use this bow
to crush the invaders?
It seems to be as powerful
as a war maiden's weapon.
I'm not sure
what it's capable of
or if I can control it...
Sometimes I black out from it.
[TIGRE] So I use its power
only as a last resort.
Then you won't be using it
much at all in these battles.
The Supreme Commander
can't black out
while fighting an army
of forty thousand.
You'll lose before
you can even wake up.
[TIGRE] I'm sorry.
That's how it is.
Don't worry. I'm sure
there will be plenty of
other opportunities to
see your powers in action.
I'll leave my fighting terms
with your bookkeepers.
But, since I know
you have nothing right now,
you can think of
my services as a loan.
So... she's onboard?
Yes, we made a deal.
[GERARD]
We just might survive.
Maybe.
Now how do you manage to
pull all this off, Count Vorn?
[GERARD]
You don't have any riches
or real political power.
And yet, starting with
Eleonora Viltaria,
you've won them over,
one after the other!
The secret is virtue.
Well, since you're
feeling so virtuous,
can I ask you to meet
with one other person tonight?
Hello?
[gasps]
My men are worried that
you're not feeling well.
You have to
try eating something.
Be careful,
it's still really hot.
Why don't I try some first?
Oh, that's good!
My lord, can I please
have your bowl of soup?
Uh, I guess.
This was supposed to be
my dinner, though.
It's so warm and tasty.
[TIGRE] What's your name?
[GIRL] Regin.
Nice to meet you, Regin.
That's a lot shorter
than my name.
[REGIN]
Count Tigrevurmud, right?
You can just call me Tigre
for short; it's easier.
Tigre...
I feel better now that
you've eaten something.
So... have a good night, Regin.
[REGIN] My lord, wait!
What is it?
There's a favor
I must ask of you.
Though my eyes may be
of different colors...
...the view they see
is unchanged.
[horse neighs]
[horse galloping]
[LEBUS KNIGHT 9A] My Lady!
The scouts have returned!
They report a force of
three thousand to the south.
Their banner?
[LEBUS KNIGHT 9A]
They have two.
Paired swords on a yellow field,
and a silver flash on black.
Why, hello, Elen.
[NARRATOR] The united forces
of Legnica and Leitmeritz,
commanded by Lady Eleonora
and the army of Lebus,
led by Lady Elizaveta,
confront each other
in Boroslow, the northeast
region of Legnica.
[SASHA] I want you to
protect Elen for me.
After all this time,
it's probably not something
I even need to ask,
but I wanted to say it
out loud anyway so you
know how serious this is.
I fear Elen may have
chosen a path
that proves even more
dangerous than usual.
There are sure to be those
who disagree with her.
They will try to stand in
her way and plot against her.
And then, it won't be her
trusty Arifal that protects her.
[SASHA] It will be people.
But how...?
You have stood by Elen's
side for a long time, Lim.
First as mercenaries, and when
she became a war maiden,
so asking you to do this
seems the most natural course.
Please protect Elen, Lim.
[LIM] I will protect her
with everything I have.
♪
Hm!
Forward, men!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Humph...
No time for talk, huh?
Follow me, men!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
I'm coming, Eleonora!
No, Lim!
Elizaveta is mine to fight!
You lead the men!
Be careful, my Lady!
[weapons clanging]
[ELIZAVETA chuckles]
Now I realize how I've
missed you, Elen.
[ELEN] I don't remember
ever giving you permission
to call me by that name!
Ley Admos!
Don't be so petty.
I wouldn't be mad if
you called me Liza...
[ELIZAVETA] Elen!
Just a warning, Elen.
The more you resist me now,
the more it'll hurt later.
Don't threaten me.
It won't end well for you.
[ELEN] Compared to
the fighting in Brune,
this is pretty easygoing.
Listen up!
Soldiers of Legnica!
[LIM] Avenge your homeland
against the invaders from Lebus!
[LIM] The best thing
I can do to protect my Lady
is to win this battle
as quickly as possible.
Verni!
[ELEN groans]
She's strong.
It doesn't take much
to turn you from cocky
to terrified, does it?
Don't be so quick to think
you've won this fight!
[ELEN yelling]
Mow down, air and all!
Ley... Admos!
Fierce claws...
Leveling heaven and Earth!
Gron Lazrihga!
Well... Looks like
we're evenly matched.
[gasps]
You managed to
push me back. Heh.
Perhaps you can
beat me, after all.
[ELEN] I'm glad that arrogant
head can still be rational.
[ELIZAVETA] Don't you have
more urgent things to do
than trade blows and
insults with me, Elen?
[gasps]
While you've been off on your
little military adventure,
the armies of Dukes
Thenardier and Ganelon
have been mobilizing.
Until recently, they had been
[ELIZAVETA] keeping each
other in check, but...
Duke Ganelon's moving out
his men as we speak.
There's one thing
I don't know, however.
Who is the military target
they're moving against?
Duke Ganelon?
Don't tell me you've--
Oh, one other thing...
Muozinel is taking advantage
of events and invading Brune
with an army numbering
almost forty thousand.
So once again I'd say
you shouldn't waste your
precious time
worrying about me.
If you want my head,
you're welcome to
keep up this sideshow.
[ELIZAVETA] But know this,
even if I'm dead,
my soldiers aren't going to
just lie down and surrender.
[grunts]
[ELIZAVETA laughs]
You don't trust a
word I'm saying.
Very well, how about this:
We exchange a written pledge.
[ELEN] Are you serious?
Yes, a pledge to
withdraw troops and begin
formal negotiations
regarding the pirates.
How about the first term
be that you and I agree to
a non-aggression pact
with each other for one year?
I want to add one condition.
And what might that be?
Say you're sorry to Sasha.
I'll spare you
from having to grovel,
but I do want a sincere,
honest apology.
Very well. As you wish.
[NARRATOR] And with that,
the Battle of Boroslow
comes to an end.
Both armies withdraw, to lay
the groundwork for a new peace.
And with the
Legnican Army helping to
speed their journey,
the next morning sees Ellen
and her forces
leave for Leitmeritz.
[ELEN] Don't do anything rash,
Tigre. We're coming.
--[MILA] Just one battle.
--[TIGRE gasps]
[MILA] We will defeat the
Muozinellan invasion force
in just one battle.
[RYURIK] You think we can?
[MILA] It's not about whether
or not "we can." We have to.
[TIGRE] Sounds like Elen.
[MILA clears throat]
Another demerit!
I know we've been at this
for a while and you're tired,
but you're responsible
for thousands of men!
Listen during war councils!
Sorry!
All right,
let's go over it again.
[MILA] Your soldiers probably
only have the strength
to manage one more battle.
It's not that I'm blaming them,
[MILA] I just hope
this isn't too reckless.
Well... we are
used to taking risks...
As long as
you think it can work.
It's the best move
we have. Just like when
you fought against the army
of twenty thousand.
[MILA]
When you're outnumbered,
wear down their strength
by attacking their supplies,
or kill their commander.
In this case, hitting
their provisions won't work.
They'd wipe us out
before we even got close
to their supply train.
Seems to me that you're
describing a job for
Sir Tigrevurmud's bow.
Perhaps, but this enemy
commander has real talent.
Wait, you've
heard of him before?
Yes, his name is
Shahin Balamir.
He also goes by
the nickname "Barbaros,"
and he's the brother of
the Muozinellan king.
So he's famous?
Must be, judging by
how she talks about him.
[MILA]
Oh for crying out loud, Tigre!
Hasn't Eleonora been
teaching you anything
about statecraft
and politics?!
I guess not.
I believe it happened
ten years ago.
Basically, Sachstein built
a navy of a thousand ships
to invade Muozinel.
When this force
entered Muozinellan waters,
he beat them with
just two hundred ships.
[TIGRE] He won?!
[MILA] Overwhelmingly!
All of the survivors trembled
at the very thought of him,
and so, out of respect and fear,
dubbed him "Red Beard."
It's Barbarossa,
in the Sachstein language,
but when translated
back to Muozinellan,
this became shortened
to simply "Barbaros."
This is the enemy commander
we must do battle
with and defeat.
So listen closely...
because we will win
where others have lost.
[TIGRE] I see.
It just might work.
But you're right
to call it reckless.
[MILA] Losing your nerve?
[TIGRE exhales] Mm-mmm.
Tell me, why are you
sticking out your neck this far?
It's simple. Because I'm
confident you're capable of
repaying a loan this great.
[MILA] And I hope
the way you pull it all off
leaves me feeling very...
satisfied.
Good luck, Tigre.
[NARRATOR] Following their
scouting party's reconnaissance,
the main Muozinellan force
marches straight down
the Agnes royal road.
The forty thousand
man army is divided into
seven divisions,
which maintain a set distance
between each other
as they advance.
By doing so,
they have the flexibility
to handle ambushes
and flanking attacks.
This is an innovation
originally devised by
Red Beard Kureys.
[KUREYS]
Let me think about this...
Whether they be an army of
Zhcted soldiers or Brunishmen,
how will they
reveal themselves?
They still haven't
appeared, have they?
[KUREYS ADVISOR 9B]
There is some news, my lord.
The envoy we sent to
the Zhcted has returned.
Good! I've been
waiting for this!
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A] My lord,
they ask that I deliver
their message orally.
I shall now recite it.
[KUREYS] Mm.
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A] "The
reason we have marched here
from our homeland
in Zhcted..."
[KUREYS] Yes...
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A]
"is because a Brunish nobleman
has asked for our support
in his civil war."
[KUREYS] And...
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A] "This,
in contrast, to your army,
which has moved
into Brune, unlawfully."
[KUREYS] What?
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A]
"We would take no pleasure
in going to war against you.
But if you continue to
threaten our Brunish ally,
we will have no choice
but retaliate."
[KUREYS] Right.
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A]
"Without further incident,
turn around and return
from whence you came."
[KUREYS] Yeah, yeah.
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A]
And that's all.
[KUREYS] In other words...
Leave if you know
what's good for you
and you won't get
a sword through your gut.
Thank you for
remembering that
long-winded ramble--
you may go.
[KUREYS MESSENGER 9A]
Yes, sire.
As much as it pains
me to admit it,
the war maiden's
accusations are correct.
Muozinel has no legal right
under any treaty or agreement
to move into Brunish land.
For all intents and purposes,
I am clearly the aggressor at
the head of an invading army.
Ha! However morally correct
the Brunish perspective,
the Zhcted still have no right
to point their fingers.
[MUOZINELLAN SOLDIER 9A]
Sire... There are two low hills
directly west of
the road in front of us.
The enemy's taken up position
behind the nearer of the two.
To the northwest,
we've also discovered
a commoner camp of
two thousand former slaves
they liberated from Kaseem.
The people of Muozinel
will lose all respect for us
if we turn away after being
threatened by a war maiden.
All right then,
Ludmila Laurie...
We're staying here.
Let's see which army it is
that conquers Brune!
[intense music plays]
Don't worry, we'll win.
We must.
[NARRATOR] Snow starts to fall,
sometime late in the morning.
Once it stops, the battle,
which will be known as
the Ormea Campaign,
will turn a perfect field
of white to red.
[MILA] We'll both
stay here and fight.
Together, okay?
[MILA] Episode Ten:
"The Ormea Campaign."
Don't watch.