[Hakkai] Goku,
please be careful.
I don't want you
dropping our food.
[Goku] Stop worrying, Hakkai.
Gyah!
[Gojyo] Dumbass.
[Hakkai] Don't be
too hard on him.
He's probably just
worried about Sanzo.
Devil meets his match, eh?
[Hakkai] This is a long rain...
[Goku] "Waiting out the storm."
[Door opens]
[Goku] You still awake?
Why don't you lie down, Sanzo?
It might help if you laid off
the cigarettes for a while.
I bought you some cough drops.
And a mask!
And a can of peaches.
If you want, I'll
open it for ya.
[Sanzo] I'm not sick.
What?
But... I can tell
something's not right.
I told you! You shouldn't smoke.
C'mere.
No fever.
I told you, I'm not sick.
[Goku] Then what is it? Tell me!
You don't eat, you don't talk,
you've been acting all weird.
There must be some reason
you're acting this way.
[Goku] It's got nothing
to do with you.
[Goku] Yes, it does!
Come on. Sanzo, tell me.
What's wrong with you?
Shut up.
What? What did-
[Sanzo] Get out.
Sanzo... you really got
me worried about you.
Why are you here?
I told you to get out!
Goku?
[Gojyo] Hey! Where
ya goin' monkey?
[Hakkai] Goku!
[Gojyo] Don't get so worked up.
He always gets like this.
I had thought of that as well.
Damn...
[Hakkai] We can't leave him
alone like this either.
[Knocking at the door]
[Door opens]
If only... the rain
would let up soon.
Then you would
feel better... right?
Don't treat me like I'm sick.
[Hakkai] I know this because...
rain does this to me too.
[Goku] What's with
the attitude?
What am I? Just a-
All alone, Son Goku?
Go away.
I'm in a really bad mood, okay?
So leave me alone.
That so?
I swear I'll kill you.
I'm warning you!
What's the matter, Goku?
Someone picking on you?
Damn you!
[Hakkai] If you feel you can
eat something, please do so.
I'll be by later to
pick up the dishes.
[Homura] You're still weak.
Far too weak.
I'll kill YOU!
[Homura] What's the
matter, Son Goku?
You use to be so much
stronger than this.
You want me?
Recall your true form.
Seiten Taisei Son Goku.
[Bones popping,
Goku yells in pain]
[Gojyo] So the monkey
never came back?
It looks that way.
[Gojyo] It's not letting up.
[Hakkai] Where you going?
[Gojyo] Cigarettes.
[Hakkai] But we
still have plenty.
[Gojyo] I'm particular
about my brands.
[Goku] If this place were
deep within the earth...
I would not yearn for
a sun I never knew.
[Homura] Are you awake?
You bastard!
[Homura] Be sure to
grit your teeth now.
[Bone popping]
[Goku] Oooow!
Damn... you!
What do you want?
Nothing.
Why don't you just
kill me? Why the-
Hey, Homura!
Damn it! Let me go, you bastard!
[Gojyo] Looks like
he got in a scuffle.
[Zenon] You lookin'
for that pipsqueak?
Give it up.
[Gojyo] What'd you say?
You're not gonna get him back.
Homura's got him now.
[Gojyo] But his highness
already has you blokes.
What's he need another pet for?
[Zenon] You're a funny guy.
[Gojyo] Tell me what
you did with him!
[Zenon chuckles]
Tell me!
[Hakkai] Did he say
Homura has him?
[Gojyo] Huh? Yeah. Why?
[Hakkai] Sounds like he's
still alive at least.
Probably, but...
What are we going to
do about it, Sanzo?
We can't just let people
come and take our monkey
whenever they feel like it.
Not without paying
for it, anyway.
[Hakkai] Sanzo.
[Sanzo] Leave it be.
[Hakkai] What?
I see no reason to get him back.
[Gojyo] What's up with that?
You don't actually think
Goku betrayed us, do you?
[Sanzo] Betrayed?
It's not like Goku actually
owes us anything.
[Gojyo] Hey, now...
[Hakkai] Do what you want.
We're going to look for Goku.
[Gojyo] We are? Hey!
[Hakkai] Sanzo, please wait
here in case Goku returns.
And I do understand why
you're acting this way.
You may not admit
it to yourself now,
but you probably feel pretty
bad for how you lashed out
at poor Goku earlier.
But this isn't going to solve
anything either, you know that.
How's the shoulder?
You look a little hungry.
Look here.
This is for you.
Don't be stubborn.
Why are you so afraid?
[Goku] I'm not afraid!
It isn't Sanzo that
you fear, is it?
[Goku] I'm no one's slave!
I'm not afraid of anything!
[Homura chuckles]
Is that so?
What about on that
mountain, Goku?
Did you laugh at your prison?
Did you curse the petty
gods who put you there?
Are you pleased to have
your memories locked away?
[Goku] Bastard...
[Homura] Don't you wanna
have your powers back?
[Goku] I can do it myself.
I don't need you for that!
[Homura] What if you can't?
Remember...
You are a heresy, just as I am.
A solitary, abominable
existence.
[Goku] No, I'm...
[Homura] That's why
you cling to Sanzo.
Because he validates
your existence.
[Goku] No!
What about Sanzo?
Does he... need you?
Have you ever been anything
other than his... servant?
Just shut up.
[Homura] You're far more
important than that.
I can see that you sense it too.
How lonely you must feel.
[Goku] I don't understand...
What do you want me to do?!
[Homura] You don't
have to do anything.
[Goku] But!
Let me protect you.
Protect me?!
I'll give you everything
you desire.
All you have to do
is come with me.
You're crazy! Like hell!
Like hell I will!
But... why?
You are coming... Son Goku?
[Gojyo] Damn that monkey
for making us hunt for
him in the rain.
What is it?
So I guess you don't
have any doubts.
What?
About why Goku hasn't come back.
You don't think Goku's in
cahoots with Homura, do you?
No. Then again...
[Gojyo] What's there
to think about?
The one thing that primate
doesn't have the stomach
for is betrayal.
Not to mention the brains.
[Zenon laughing]
Up there!
[Zenon] Their playful
banter is so adorable.
[Shien] You shouldn't mock
the poor things, Zenon.
[Gojyo] Stop screwing around!
What'd you do with Goku?!
Nothin'.
I thought I told you guys...
Homura's got 'im. Get over it.
We'll just keep looking
for him, if you don't mind.
How very laudable of you.
Shit.
[Shien] So they are
persistent, aren't they?
[Hakkai] I've been told it's
one of my finer virtues.
[Zenon] There's not much virture
in being dead now, is there?
[Gojyo] I'm afraid dying
has never been one of
my strong suits.
[Homura] You'll only fight this
valiantly so you can keep Goku's
power all to yourselves.
Power?
Come on, don't be silly.
He's just a stupid monkey.
Besides, if you guys
take him away from us...
then we can't play mah-jongg.
Tell me what you did with Goku!
[Homura] That is none
of your business!
[Hakkai] What did you say?!
Gojyo!
AAAH!
Hakkai!
[Hakkai] Sanzo!
I couldn't sleep.
Lonely without your Goku, eh?
[Sanzo] An idle spectator?
What a nuisance.
[Goku] If this place had been
deep within the earth...
I never would have had to know
freedom... and loneliness.
Come back here!
Sanzo, you're the mean one!
You don't care about me at all!
What's wrong if I worry about
you every once in a while?!
If I knew it was going to be
like this when I got out,
I would have asked you
to leave me there!
I'm always causing you nothing
but trouble. I hate that...
What am I to you?
I really wanna know...
Just tell me.
Hey, what the hell did
you say to him, anyway?
Nothing.
[Homura] Sanzo, Son Goku needs
the light of your wisdom.
'Cause it appears that
I cannot be his sun.
When I come again,
I will take him by force.
Farewell.
Later.
[Sanzo] I'm in a bad mood
because of the rain.
The rest you'll have to
figure out for yourself.
Sanz...
[Goku] He led me out
of the darkness...
He showed me a world... much...
much brighter than the sun.
[Sanzo] I never wanted
you to be a servant.
[Hakkai] Shall we get going?
[Gojyo] How far
are we going today?
[Hakkai] I could use something
to snack on if we're gonna
be on the road for a while.
[Sanzo] Hey. Go buy some
pickled kelp and frozen
mandarin oranges.
[Goku] Why do I have
to go get 'em?
[Sanzo] Because I'll kill
you if you don't do it.
[Goku] I thought you said
I wasn't your servant?
[Goku yells] I'm going,
I'm going!
[Gojyo] Man, you
are so twisted.
[Sanzo] Who you calling twisted?
[Gojyo] No one! Watch it!
[Hakkai laughs] Glad to see
everyone's in a good mood
now that the sun's out.