[Sanzo] You know, I have
to admit I'm really not
up for this today.
[Hakkai] You'd think they'd
realize it's pointless by now.
[Demons growling]
[Gojyo] Maybe we could
make a game out of it.
Help hold our interest
a little bit.
[Sanzo] I bet I could knock out
the next wave before they
reach the halfway mark.
I never knew you had a
playful side to you, monk.
[Demons yell and growl]
That's a good way
to relieve stress.
You need that, too.
[Hakkai chuckles]
What's keeping Goku anyway?
He's missing all the fun.
Did ya miss me?
[Goku] "Scripture Raiders."
Oh no...
[Homura] I was bound and
tortured for being a heretic.
A little splotch in their
white-washed paradise.
And then, the one I
loved was taken from me.
So I rebelled against
the Heavens with the
same scorn they showed me.
And what have I gained?
Why do I wage this war?
To create a new
Heaven and Earth?
Or is it...
something else?
[Zenon] You're finally ready,
aren't you?
[Homura] Yeah.
So, the time has come.
[Zenon] No explanations.
No motivational speeches.
Just say the word, man.
[Shien] If you're ready,
there's only one thing we
need to hear from you.
[Homura] Zenon...
[Zenon] Yo.
[Homura] Shien...
[Shien] Yes.
[Homura] Let's go. It's time.
[Demon yells]
Beat that, guys!
Did I just see that? All
those demons in five minutse?
I don't know why we bother
fighting at all anymore.
Pretty soon we'll just sit back
and let him do all the work.
Soon he won't need
us at all. Freaky.
Hey, are you alright?
Sanzo?
[Sanzo] Yeah. Sure.
SO, how did I do?
Did I win? Did I?
What should we get? Eggrolls?
Lo Mein? Peking duck?
Or how about I nice big Tianjin
bowl, with a side of meat buns?
[Goku] Yeah!
[Gojyo] Everything you
listed is Chinese food.
[Goku] Huh? You're kidding.
[Gojyo] Good grief.
[Hakkai] What does it matter?
At this point, I could eat just
about anything.
[Sanzo] Moron.
[Hakkai] What?
No paper fan today?
[Sanzo] Hmph. I don't
have the energy.
[Hakkai] Look, Sanzo
, you're going to totally
look like an old man
if you're tense all the time.
You should learn to relax a
little bit. It wouldn't kill ya.
I could never afford to let
my guard down for a minute.
Huh?
[Goku] Huh?
Not again.
[Zenon] So how's it gonna be?
If we throw down here, we might
destroy the entire city.
Well, not that it matters
to us either way, right?
[Gojyo] Hey buddy, your pick.
It doesn't matter to us either.
[Sanzo] What is it
you want this time?
[Hakkai] Or is it too
presumptuous to assume
that this isn't a coincidence?
[Homura] Toying with you
guys doesn't amuse me anymore.
So...
this will be your last chance to
hand over the Maten Scripture...
without incident.
[Sanzo] Is that so?
[Homura] You should know...
[Homura] If it comes to
a fight, there'll be no
mercy for you this time.
[Sanzo] So, you've finally
decided to get serious?
[Goku] Let's hop to it! I want
to get this over before the
restaurants close!
You have until morning.
Oh boy, here we go.
I expect your answer
first thing tomorrow.
Stop your stalling. You already
know our answer to that.
Please, take your time.
Sleep on it.
By the way, there's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
What's that?
This superiority act of yours...
is pissing me off.
Has it been so long...
that you've forgotten, Konzen?
What do you mean?
[Homura chuckles]
Surely you must remember
what Heaven is like.
When you're stuck up there,
you've got all the time
in the universe.
You don't want the fun to
be over with too quickly.
Especially when the game
just got interesting.
[Gojyo] Don't wait around
for us too long tomorrow.
We re pretty bad about
keeping our appointments.
[Shien] Are you planning to run?
[Gojyo] Excuse me?
[Shien] It sounded
as if you just said
you were planning
to run from us.
[Gojyo] The hell I am.
[Hakkai] I, for one, am planning
to sleep in late tomorrow.
[Homura] Don't worry, you'll
rest in peace for a long, long
time, sleepy head.
[Gojyo] You could use a little
beauty rest yourself, cyclops.
[Zenon] I assure you I will
have no trouble sleeping
tonight.
Dreaming up ways to make
the moment last.
I might just perm that
pretty mane of yours.
Sleep tight fellas. This is
gonna be your last night
on Earth.
[Homura] I'm looking
forward to it.
[Gojyo] This does not
sit well with me.
[Goku] What do you mean?
It's delicious!
[Gojyo] Will you just shut
up and eat! I'm talking
about Hamura!
[Goku] Hey! You don't
have to ask me twice.
[Hakkai] I feel like the mouse
the cat plays with before
it's going to kill it.
Why don't they just
take what they want?
It should be easy enough for
someone with their powers.
[Gojyo] Either they're really
confident, really polite,
or really bored...
[Hakkai] I'm gonna go out
on a limb here and say
all of the above.
[Gojyo] Or this could be their
way of flirting with one of us.
[Hakkai] We know they're after
the Maten Scripture.
That gives us a foundation from
which to build our defenses.
[Gojyo] Defenses? More like
defenseless, if you ask me.
I don't care if they are gods.
We eliminate anyone who's stupid
enough to stand in our way.
That's all there is to it!
[Goku] Hey, where
you going, Sanzo?
Sanzo!
[Goku] Come on! Why won't you
tell me what's bothering you?
[Sanzo] Do you have
to be such a pest?
[Goku] See? This is the way you
always act when something's
wrong. I can tell.
[Sanzo] Oh? Is that right?
[Goku] Look, I'll stop pestering
you if you buy me a meat bun!
[Sanzo] We just ate,
for crying out loud!
[Goku] I can't help it,
walking give me an appetite.
Please! Just a little one?
[Sazno] [irritated sigh] But I
just gave you... Damn.
[Goku] Yay! Meat bun! Meat bun!
[Gojyo] Hey, Hakkai.
[Hakkai] Yeah?
[Gojyo] Ah, it's nothing.
[Hakkai] Please just say it.
Otherwise I'll be wondering
about it all night.
[Gojyo] It's just... Do you
think we can take these guys?
Who knows? It sure felt like we
were outmatched in our last
encounter, if you ask me.
We'll find out, won't we?
Huh?
[gasps]
Damn you!
Not so fast, Gojyo.
It appears as if they're just
here for a drink like we are.
[Zenon] A shot of
your strongest.
[Shein] Oolong tea please.
[Zenon] And a round for our
friends over there.
[Gojyo] I don't like the crowd
here, Hakkai!
Let's find some place that
doesn't leave a bad taste
in my mouth.
[Zenon] Ease back on the
testosterone. The fight's
tomorrow remember?
[Gojyo] I've never
been very patient.
[Shein] What an oaf.
[Gojyo] Say what?
I knew someone who often
spoke like that.
[Kenren] Flowers are great.
Women are better.
But a glass of good
rice win is heaven.
[Shein] I can never know the
pleasures of a good wine,
but I do think I know what that
man was trying to say.
[Gojyo] Hmph. I'd like to meet
this guy sometime.
So, any chance of introducing
an oaf like me to some of these
women you've been talking about,
oh illustrious one?
[Shein] I'm afraid I don't know
any women, but there are some
flowers right there.
[Gojyo] Pretty neat trick.
What is this?
Fattening the bird before
sending him to the slaughter?
[Hakkai] It doesn't matter.
This little situation will all
be settled in the morning.
Isn't that right?
[Zenon] Well put, my friend.
Well put indeed.
[Goyjo] That about sums it.
[Zenon] Who know what the new
day brings.
[Gojyo] I'll drink to that.
Damnit. It's no use.
I can't sleep.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow's the big day.
[Sanzo] Can't sleep?
[Goku] No.
[Goku] Say, Sanzo.
You think the weather will
be good tomorrow?
[Sanzo] That settles it.
You are an idiot.
[Goku] Why am I an idiot?
I was just...
[Sanzo] Just what?
[Goku] I just can't wait.
All I can think about is bashing
Homura's face in tomorrow.
[Goku] I'm going crazy.
[Sanzo] It's not like it's your
birthday, you know.
I know that. It's just, I
think I can really beat him.
Just go to sleep, will ya?
Judging by the evening sky,
it looks like it should be
a nice day tomorrow.
Homura, the day is mine.
[Homura] I'm waiting.
What is you reply?
[Sanzo] Go shopping for
scriptures elsewhere, scum.
[Homura] Are you sure this
is how you want it?
Well it's your show, Goku.
Remember that it's the Maten
Scripture they're after.
So what that means is, I have
to get them before they get
us. Right?
That's about what it comes
down to, yes.
That's what it always comes
down to, isn't it?
What ever happens,
happens. Fine.
[Zenon] So, can we get this
little party started now?
[Shein] I think we have delayed
for long enough.
Let the battle begin.
I haven't forgotten our
last meeting, Homura.
Grow stronger...
You must grow stronger,
Son Goku.
Well, Homura, today you get
your wish.
Let's see how strong
I really am!
Come and get me!
Homura!
Ready to rumble?
We're coming for you now.
Eat lead!
[Hakkai] Aw come on. You're
gonna have to do better
than that.
I will.
Don't forget about the rest
of us standing over here,
you morons.
[Homura] Such speed and
power, his skills have
certainly improved.
It's as if he's a completely
different person.
Son Goku, with this...
[Goku] Homura, what are
you looking at?!
What?!
It's over!
Now now. What kind of loyal,
trusted henchman would I be if I
let you touch him that easily?
Homura!
Goku!
[Both] Homura!
I- I hit him.
Looks like you pass the test.
Not so fast!
[Zenon] That's my line.
This'll slow him down!
That won't do.
Konzen!
[Sanzo] I've had enough of this!
Damn!
Sanzo!
You're still resisting?
That I am.
In that case...
So it comes to an end.
I'll take this if you
don't mind, Konzen.
And, General Kenren,
be sure to let Goku know,
if he wants the Maten Scripture
it will be waiting for him in
the Tower of Konran.
That so?!
I'll be waiting.
[Sanzo] Homura!
You... bastard...
You!
Son of a...
...bitch.
Sanzo!
That's what I like about
you, Konzen.
Zenon, Shien, let's go.
Sanzo!
[Gojyo] Sanzo!