[Kougaiji] A rumor?
[Yaone] Yes. For the past few
weeks, we have heard the exact
same story coming from several
completely different sources.
Furthermore, we have confirmed
that thirty demons have indeed
gone missing as the rumors
suggest. And just the other
day, eight more demons suddenly
vanished overnight.
[Kougaiji] Eight? Overnight?
Please. Tell me this rumor
[Goku] "The Truth of Justice"
[Man] Help me! Ahhhh!
[Kazuki] Don't look so sad.
The stronger much always
root out the weaker.
It's the natural order.
[Demon] She's a real look-er.
She's got nice legs.
It's not just the legs, it's
the curve from her
neck to her shoul-
Hey!
[Kougaiji] So, what
does this mean?
[Yaone] Lord Kougaiji, I'll
go investigate the matter.
[Kougaiji] No.
[Dokugakuji] Here we go again,
you're so over-protective.
[Kougaiji] I am not!
[Lirin] You never change,
do you, Kougaiji?
At any rate, I think someone
should look into this.
I'm willing to go down and
scout it out, if you'd like.
Check it out, but that's it!
Return as soon as you
find the cause. Reporting
back is your first priority!
I...
[Dokugakuji] Good grief.
It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
C'mon, when are we going
to get there Hakkai?
[Hakkai] Just a little longer.
A town should be
coming into view soon.
You keep saying that, but
I'm gonna turn into jerky
by the time we get there!
And I doubt anyone would
buy stringy monkey jerky.
Take that back!
How long are we going to be
stuck with this drab view?
Just sky and sand as
far as the eye can see.
Huh?
What the heck is that?
[Gojyo] Boy, you've got
to be devoted to wear that
armor in this weather.
[Goku] Hey, Sanzo, what do
you think they're up to?
[Sanzo] How the
hell should I know?
[Gojyo] Who are
these guys anyway?
They're a sorry-looking
bunch, if you ask me.
They're the Special Anti-
Demon Unit, Huanglong.
[Gojyo] Huanglong?
A private human army that
specializes in fighting demons.
Well, I suppose they're
more like bounty
hunters than an army.
They're a group of mercenaries
who hire out their services
to towns and villages to
solve their demon problems
for them. For a price.
Well let's go. The
marching band's got
nothing to do with us.
We're wasting our time.
[Gojyo & Goku] Okay.
[Tongpu] Hey, Hakkai! Gojyo!
[Goku] Who's that?
[Gojyo] Couldn't say.
They're not the kind of crowd
I usually hang out with, yanno.
Hey guys! Remember me? It's
Tongpu! We used to live
in the same town together!
Tongpu! Is that really
you, my old friend?
Of course it's me, you dope!
Tongpu! You used to play a mean
game of mah-jongg at the parlor!
[Tongpu] Yeah, I'm the one! I'm
glad you guys still remember me!
[Hakkai] So Tongpu, what are
you doing wandering around
the middle of the desert?
After a few thousand games
of mah-jongg, I realized
I didn't want to be stuck
out in the boondocks forever.
Ah yes. Same here.
[Tongpu] I suppose I wanted to
do my part and straighten out
the shit that's been happening.
Maybe make a few bucks too. So I
signed up and joined Huanglong.
I haven't been with
them long, though.
[Soldier] Tongpu, fall
back in formation!
Uh. Yes, Sir!
[Tongpu] Hey, we've still've
a lot of catching up to do,
so how about we get together
tomorrow and do it properly?
It'll be just like the old days!
If I can get some time off.
I know a bar in the next town
with some good home-brewed sake!
[Gojyo] I'm all about that.
[Tongpu] See you tomorrow!
[Gojyo] You bet!
[Goku] Huanglong, huh? They
could have come up with
a better name than that.
[Gojyo] Boy, he sure
hasn't changed at all.
Has he, Hakkai?
[Hakkai] Do you think so?
He never stuck me as the
type who would join a
mercenary outfit.
[Gojyo] You say it like
it's a bad thing.
It's a respectable enough
profession, but it's too much
discipline for my taste though.
So you don't have any
problem with them?
[Sanzo] It just means that
humans aren't going to
take this lying down.
This looks right.
[Yaone gasp]
[Commander] So how do
you like the view?
You've got a lot of guts
coming all the way out here
by yourself, demon woman.
But I'm afraid you ought
to have taken us...
a lot more seriously.
Then again, that might
be too much to ask of
your puny demon brain.
So you are the ones killing
demons that I've been
hearing about.
[Commander] At your service.
We never go hungry, with all
you demons around to slay.
I will not allow you to
get away with this madness.
Get her!
[Yaone] Noooo!
[Footsteps approaching]
[Commander] Awake, are we?
You bastard!
Yes, there you go.
You just struggle all you want.
Talk! I want to know
who you really are!
I can tell just by
looking at you, you're
not just any demon!
Fine. Have it your way.
I would have been disappointed
if you had talked before I got
a chance to have my fun.
[Yaone] Lord Kougaiji...
[Dokugakuji] It's way past
time for her to report
in, what's keeping her?
[Lirin] Kougaiji, do you
think something has happened
to Yaone? Kougaiji!
[Dokugakuji] Hey.
[Kougaiji] Dokugakuji, saddle up
the flight dragon!
[Gojyo] Well then, here's
to a memorable reunion.
[Everyone] Cheers!
[Goku] This looks
good! Let's eat!
[Tongpu] So what's it
been now, three years?
[Gojyo] Boy, has it? So, what
have you been up to, Tongpu?
Do you enjoy playing the
proper champion of justice?
[Tongpu] I don't have any
actual combat experience yet.
But, I train everyday.
And they work us like dogs.
Sounds like hard work.
Don't you ever worry that
there are some demons out
there that you don't even
stand a chance against?
No, that's what our
training is for.
Besides, I heard...
I heard a rumor that the
higher-ups have gotten
hold of... something.
A some sort of top
secret weapon.
A top secret weapon, huh?
We're definitely seeing a lot
more demons around here lately.
As a matter of fact, one
demon attacked the camp
just the other evening.
A good looking one too.
But here's the weird
thing. She was walking
through the camp alone.
[Hakkai] Alone?
[Tongpu] Yeah.
She attacked us with
spears and bombs.
Capturing her wasn't
easy, let me tell you.
[Gojyo] Spears and bombs, huh?
[Tongpu] What's wrong?
[Hakkai] Nothing.
I was just wondering what
happened to her. That's all.
[Tongpu] I believe they
took her to a cell somewhere.
Why? Does that bother you?
Well no, not in principle.
[Tongpu] Good, you had me
worried there for a minute.
[Sanzo] Let's get moving.
Hey! I'm not finished yet!
[Gojyo] Just finish
your octopus.
[Goku] That's what I was doing!
[Hakkai] Well it's
been fun, as always.
[Gojyo] It's good to
see you again, Tongpu.
[Tongpu] You're still
gonna be in town, right?
[Gojyo] Yeah, I'll
see you around.
[Gojyo] Yaone, right?
[Sanzo] Undoubtedly.
[Goku] What? Really?!
[Gojyo] Moron. Where
have you been?
[Goku] I'm sorry! I can't
help it! I didn't notice!
[Gojyo] That's why
you're a monkey.
[Goku] What's that
supposed to mean?
[Sanzo] You're going, aren't
you? You do realize that if you
go, you might end up having
to fight your friend.
[Hakkai] I'm not sure
what I'm going to do.
I know Yaone is technically
our enemy, and perhaps it
isn't my place to get
involved in this.
But...
I couldn't live with myself if
I left without doing something.
Besides, if I go, there's
no guarantee that I'd
have to fight Tongpu.
[Hakkai] And so...
[Gojyo] You want us to
come with you, right?
[Goku] Isn't that right, Hakkai?
[Hakkai] Right!
[Gojyo] Well, now
that's decided.
Let's go raid us a camp.
[Sanzo] Wait.
[Goku] What? Sanzo...
I think we should
sneak in at night.
Best not to take any
unnecessary chances with
these two idiots in tow.
Right.
[Gojyo] Haha, you hear that?
He called you an idiot.
[Goku] He called you one too!
[Gojyo] What?! Hey Sanzo, what
do you mean TWO idiots?!
[Sanzo] Exactly what
it sounds like.
I believe this is
the place, huh?
[Gojyo] Quite an operation
they got going here.
It won't be easy tracking
down one person.
[Goku] So, what's the plan?
[Hakkai] Let's split
up and search for her.
We won't stand out
so much that way.
[Gojyo] Okay. I'll check
you guys later.
[Goku] Shit!
[Soldier] Who's there?!
[Loud thud]
[Gojyo] Hey, monkey. The
idea was to sneak in here,
not barge in and cause a ruckus.
Do you comprende?
[Goku] I know that!
[Gojyo] You know what,
I don't think you do.
[Goku] Look, I don't need
to hear it from you!
[Tongpu] Hakkai?
[Hakkai] Tongpu...
[Tongpu] What're you doing here?
[Hakkai] I, uh...
[Tongpu] You're not here to...
[Hakkai] To what?
[Hakkai] Sorry friend, but
I'm in a hurry. I'm sorry.
Yaone!
[Dokugakuji] Kou, be
careful. These guys know
what they're doing.
[Kougaiji] Yaone!
[Yaone] What are you doing here?
We can talk later. Right
now, let's get out of here.
This... This is...
Horrible.
[Goku] Hey... Kougaiji!
[Gojyo] What?
Take me to Yaone.
[Commander] I don't
know who that is.
That's too bad for you. Now I
have no use for you anymore.
[Hakkai] Yaone is right here.
[Dokugakuji] Not you again.
[Kougaiji] Yaone?
[Sanzo] I believe you came
here for Yaone. Here she is.
[Kougaiji] Why if
it isn't Sanzo.
[Lirin] And the
droopy-eyed monkey!
[Sanzo] If you want
her, take her. This fight
is as good as over.
It appears we like to
frequent the same hangouts.
Very well then. I suggest you
hand Yaone over right now!
Okay. I'm coming. Let's
just take this slow and-
T-Tongpu...
This is all your fault!
Tongpu, you damn bastard!
You're dead meat, buddy!
[Hakkai] It's all right!
[Goku] Ha-Hakkai...
I'm so sorry...
[Tongpu] What the hell
is wrong with you guys?!
Helping demon scum?!
Just whose side you think
you're on anyway?!
We don't fight for either side.
I... was just..
I was just trying to
help a dear friend of
mine who was in trouble.
[Goku] Hakkai!
[Hakkai] Kougaiji, I believe
I have returnedYaone to you.
Yeah.
[Gojyo] Uh oh.
Did you know the one who's
been bathed in the blood
of a thousand demons becomes
a demon himself?! It doesn't
matter how much! Bathe in
it and this is what you get!
Say your prayers!
He's a monster!
Who's the demon now?
It's your own fault
for being too soft and
weak to finish me off.
Now you can all prepare
to join each other in hell!
He's gone insane.
Goku, Gojyo, let's go!
You guys stand back. We can take
care of this guy, no problem.
What're you planning?
I intend to repay an old debt.
[Goku] You gotta be joking!
[Gojyo] And let you
guys have all the fun?
Eugh, melting stuff?!
[Goku] Damn it!
[Gojyo] Don't let down
your guard, Monkey!
[Lirin] That's why we told
you to leave it to us!
Hiiiiiiii-yah!
[Tongpu] Hakkai...
Why did you save me?
I though I told you.
I don't fight on the
side of humans or demons.
Besides you... were kind enough
not to hit anything vital.
Now, shall we settle this?
[Sanzo] Hakkai!
Will you please return to
the darkness so that you
can be with the souls of
all the demons you killed!
[Yaone] There, that
ought to do it.
You should be fine by next week.
[Hakkai] Thank you so much.
[Yaone] Not problem.
I'll thank you for what
you did today, but the
next time we meet again-
[Gojyo] We know, we know, we're
tired of hearing that already.
[Goku] Fighting would be
awkward right now anyway.
[Dokugakuji] Yeah, it just
wouldn't feel right.
[Lirin] Hey, droopy-eyes,
we'll play again later, okay?
[Sanzo] Will you go home
already, you little brat.
Yaone, it's time to go!
[Yaone] Thank you, Hakkai.
My pleasure, Yaone.
[Sanzo] Come on, let's go!
[Sanzo] You shouldn't listen
to other people who tell you
who your friends and
enemies are. Much less
let them decide for you.
It's hard enough figuring
out that for yourself.
Don't you think?
[Sanzo] A sorrowful encounter.
A future that cannot be changed.
A past that cannot
be taken back.
There is but one small
uncertain hope for us
to put our faith into.
Does the path lead
to light or darkness?
There's only one way
to know for sure.
Watch "Maidens of Sorrow",
next time on Saiyuki.