[Koushu] You do understand
that I'm counting on you people.
Do try not to disappoint
me again.
How one measly monk can cause
you so much trouble is
beyond me.
You wouldn't say that if you ver
tried fighting Sanzo yourself.
Really?
Then I take it you have no
objections to my trying a
more hands on approach.
[Kougaji] You're always welcome
to try.
[Ni] Lady Koushu,
perhaps I could interest you in
a rare piece of fruit.
[Koushu] Show me.
It might help wash away some
of the bitterness
and replace it with the sweet
taste of revenge.
"The Forbidden Fruit"
[Goku] I'm starving!
[Gojyo] We just ate for crying
out loud!
[Goku] You call that eating?
Nibbling more like.
Got some bad news.
We seem to have run out of all
our supplies.
What?!
For pete's sake, here, eat this.
Are you sure? Thank you!
Blagh! What is this?!
Used klenex.
Asswipe!
It's your fault for being so
patheticly gullible.
[Goku] This time you've really
done it!
[Gojyo] You did it to yourself.
[Goku] Eat this, dickwad!
[Gojyo] Bite me!
Something smells delicious!
[Sanzo] You've got to be joking.
[Goku] Quick, turn right here!
[Hakkai] Whoa! Let go of the
steering wheel!
[Lirin's stomach growls]
Now I'm famished.
Nature walks sure make
me hungry.
I smell something tasty!
[Lirin] Mount Dumpling.
That sounds promising.
I bet they have food up
there somewhere.
[Lirin] Ah! Not you guys again!
Prepare to meet your doom!
What the hell do you think
you're doing here?
[Lirin] What are YOU doing here?
[Goku and Lirin's
stomaches growl]
[Goku] I smelled it first!
[Lirin] I was here before you!
I swear, they have the exact
same behavior.
If I didn't know any better, I'd
say she was Goku's little
sister than Kougaiji's.
[Lirin] Yipee! What a
huge tree!
[Goku] Out of my way!
[Lirin] Hey, not fair!
Ow!
Ow! This tree branch stung me!
[Goku] What a weird tree.
Oh, well.
What the hell's going on here?
That's mine!
What the? Now it's bad.
Man, what a mean tree!
[to the tree] Will you stop
teasing me?
[Sanzo] You idiots!
What's the big idea?!
You two are trespassing in here.
You know, he's right. You should
ask the people in the temple for
permission first.
But what if they say no?
Can't you see I'm freakin'
starve to death over here?
Yeah! Besides we already tried
to eat them, but all the fruit
are rotten!
[Goku] And they smell so
tasty too.
[Gojyo] What are you wasting
your time for if they're not
even edible?
Besides, where is everybody?
[Hakkai] Hello?!
Is anybody here?!
Who are you?
[Hakkai] Just travelers are on
our way West, no one to be
suspicious about.
Despite how we look.
Don't you look at me when you
say that.
Hey, do you have anything to
eat around here?
We're really very hungry.
[Chinpu] You are travelers?
Twins?
Excuse me, are you?
You couldn't possibly be the
legenday monk Sanzo, could you?
No, you have the wrong guy.
I don't get it. Just tell them
who you are, Sanzo.
What have you got to hide?
You two are dead.
Now, now, all you have to do is
do is something Sanzo-like.
And we get free room and board.
You can put up with a little
hero worship for us, can't you,
oh elusterious one?
No, I can't.
[Chinpu] My name is Chinpu. I am
an apprentice here at Gosoukan.
[Mingetsu] I am Mingetsu.
Please come in, Priest Sanzo.
[Sanzo] [quietly] What a pain in
the ass.
[Chinpu] As you can see we
live modestly.
[Mingetsu] But please, take
what we can offer you.
What's this?
[Chinpu] It is called soukantan.
Made from ninjinka seeds.
Two are enough to make you
full. Eat.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid this
is all we have to offer you.
Well, I guess if they'll fill
me up, bon appitete.
Down the hatch!
No! Don't eat!
Why the hell not?!
So why don't I see anyone else
at this temple, huh?
Well, usually our senior
disciples are here but they...
They all left on with our
master about a month or so
ago to set off on some journey.
And you two have been watching
the temple alone all this time?
[Chinpu] Yes.
[Gojyo] I'm just surprised
you haven't been attacked by
burglars or demons since then.
That is probably only because we
have the holy powers of the
ninjinka here to protect us
from harm.
[Goku] Speaking of which, why
can't you eat them?
[Lirin] They rotted the second
we touched 'em.
You need special tools, called
kingekishi and tanban,
if you want to be able to pick
the fruit from the tree.
Besides, the fruit of the
ninjinka are not yet ripe
to pick.
[Goku] I figured that much out.
Thank you, but we must go.
You wouldn't dare make us go
without eating at least a
snack, would you?
[Sanzo] Yes, I would.
But can't we just.
[Sanzo] Never mind, let's go!
Well, I'm not in a hurry, so
I'm going to try one!
Guh tastes like puke!
[Lirin] Bye! See ya later!
What the hell is that little
girl on?
Let's go.
[Chinpu] Wait.
Please take this.
It will help to ease your hunger
while on your journey.
[Goku] Thank you! You're the
greatest!
We have not had guests in so
long. It's too bad.
We would have liked you to
stay with us until our
master returned.
But we understand.
[Sanzo] Goku, what's the
hold up?
[Gojyo] Will you get down
here, monkey!
Don't call me that!
[Goku] You two wait here for
a moment! I'll be right back.
You sensed it?
Yeah, they're definitely demons.
What do you think? Should we
go back there and take 'em out?
Who do you think we are?
Some champions of justice
or something?.
I'd just as soon not get
involved with those two.
Hey, guys! Those poor kids said
they're lonely!
Let's stay with them just a
little while!
Let's go. There's something
that's just not right about
those two.
[Goku] What do you mean?
Can't you see that the ninjinka
allows them both to cover up
their demon scent?
But take a look at what they
gave me.
Isn't it possible they're
good demons?
Goku, I don't think it's safe
to put too much faith in other
people right now.
Why should I have to
distrust people?
[Sanzo] Enough, it's pointless
trying to reason with him.
[Goku] Hey, you give that back!
It's mine!
You shut up! Your idiocy
is breath taking.
Okay, so I'm an idiot! What's
wrong with that huh?
[Gojyo] Just where in the hell
do you think you're going?
I'm going back! To prove you're
wrong about those guys!
[Hakkai] Come on, Goku!
Ugh. Should we go after him?
No. We should probably just
let him go.
It'll be useless to try and talk
to him anyway.
I'm afraid some lessons can only
be learned by living with
our mistakes.
Fine, so I may be an idiot,
but if I can never trust anyone
...I'd rather be stupid than go
on living like that.
I'm not feeling so good.
[Mingetsu] It was truly good of
you to come back. Please eat.
Right, okay, here goes!
Those are truly awful!
But I feel just dandy.
I just knew that Sanzo had
pegged you guys all wrong.
[Mingetsu] He ate it.
[Chinpu] Yes. We did well.
[Mingetsu] Too bad we let Sanzo
and the others get away.
Luckily we already collected his
DNA data. That should be enough.
Well thank you!
[Goku] I'll be going now.
You guys...
[Goku] You really are the
bad guys.
[Hakkai] Goku's certainly been
gone awhile.
[Gojyo] I suppose that means
we have to camp out in this
place, huh?
I don't mean this as an omage or
anything but I'm hungry.
Hey, look here.
[Lirin] I have to go there.
I have to go there.
[Hakkai] Lirin, where are
you going?
Lirin!
[Lirin] I have to go there.
I have to go there.
What do you make of that?
I'd say it means that...
...we should never eat these.
What's the matter?
Considering how many
seeds he ate,
the ninjinka buds should have
burst through his body long
before now.
It's the demon limiter.
It's suppressing the power of
the seeds.
Then if we take this
thing off...
Get away!
How dare you trick me?!
I trusted you!
[Goku] I promise, you'll pay
dearly for this!
And I keep my word!
[Gojyo] I had no idea it was
like this behind the mountain.
[Hakkai] So, you think maybe we
should stop her?
[Sanzo] How?
[Hakkai] Good point.
[Sanzo] So those are the roots
of the ninjinka.
[Hakkai] Will you look at that.
[Sanzo] I see, human bulbs.
[Hakkai] The plant is using
these people as fertilizer.
[Gojyo] I'm seeing double.
Then, who were the two in
the temple?
[Chingenshi] Pardon me. Could
you be Priest Sanzo?
[Sanzo] And you are?
You must pardon my manners.
I am Chingenshi.
Who serves as the head
of Gosoukan.
Truly impressive.
How do you maintain
consciousness with this
thing draining all your chi?
Oh I doubt I'll last
much longer.
The ninjinka's super natural
powers increase by the day.
Tell me what happened here.
[Goku yells]
This guy's a monster.
Someone needs to teach him when
it's time to give up!
Look, the seeds are finally
begining to take root.
[Goku] Damnit! You'll both be
fertilizer before it takes
control of me!
Various items are are often
brought here, to the temple as
religious offerings.
One day, a small sapling was
delivered my a man in glasses.
We planted it out in the yard,
but we could see immediately
that this was no ordinary tree.
It grew at such an alarming rate
that we feared the ninjinka
was created by some form of
black magic.
We tried to cut it down, but
blades could not scratch it,
and its bark was impervious
to fire.
Not knowing what else to do,
when the tree eventually
bore fruits,
I forbid my pupils to eat them,
But Chinpu and Mingetsu
disobeyed me.
Two clones were created,
and without knowing it,
they served the fruit to
us, and we wound up here.
[Mingetsu] Think you can
defeat us...
[Chinpu] ...in your
current state?
[Goku] Shut up! Will you please
stand still?!
His movements have grown
quite sluggish.
We might still have to wait
a while before he becomes
a bulb.
It's time for the next step.
Yes, we may have to use these.
What are those? Weapons?!
No, these are tools.
A kingekishi...
...and tanban.
[Hakkai] Hold it a second.
Where did you say Mingetsu
and Chinpu come from?
[Gosoukan] They are
ninjinka fruits.
It steals people's genetic codes
The grows an exact duplicate out
of their seeds.
Identical replicas.
They're clones.
When Goku and Lirin tried to
pick those fruits they...
It took a sample when they were
pricked by the ninjinka vines.
[Sanzo] If that's the case, then
even he may havemet his match.
[Goku] What?!
[Chinpu] If we had allowed her
to fully ripen,
she would have become conscious
like us.
[Mingetsu] But her powers are
the same as the real thing!
She should defeat you!
Hey, lay off of me and let's
get to the real root of
the problem!
Bitch!
You're not nearly as cute as
the real one!
Damn him!
Let's see if he fights as well
against large numbers!
Uh, this isn't good.
[Chinpu] No one can be stronger
than themselves.
[Mingetsu] Will you give up now
and become a pod-person?
It's finally sprouted.
Yes, let's seize him!
[Sanzo] Stop!
Sheesh, I thought one Goku was
bad enough.
You should think of all the
trouble they'll cause
other folks.
Besides, illegal copies are an
infringement of copyright.
S-Sanzo... Gojyo... Hakkai...
We knew you guys would come
back here for your friend.
You saved us the trouble of
chasing after you.
So these guys must be
Kougaiji's assassins?
His own sister has become root
bait. I find that unlikely.
In that case, then it's the
mastermind who's pulling all
of Kougaiji's strings.
That makes sense. The twisted
personalities seem to point in
that direction.
Ha! Useless babble.
Kill at will.
Now you're composte heap.
Ha! I like this. Beating up
a gang of monkeys feels
pretty good!
[Hakkai chuckles] I know it's
hard, but do try not to destroy
the original, will you?
For some reason, it bothers me
they're having this much fun
defeating me!
Just whose side are they
on anyway!
[Mingetsu] What?!
[Chinpu] I don't understand!
They should have the same
powers as Goku!
Don't underestimate us. Goku may
be nutty but he ain't no fruit!
The Goku we know is much
more daft!
Next time you take a DNA sample
from Goku,
you might want to make sure he's
not hungry first.
They may hang from trees but
they sure make pathetic excuses
for monkeys.
[Sanzo] Looks like you're out
of tricks.
Now end this game.
No!
Don't shoot!
What the hell? Why didn't you do
that from the very begining,
instead of having to fight
them all?
That wouldn't have
been satisfying.
[Goku] What?
[Sanzo] For you, I mean.
Now hurry up and finish the job.
Listen up, ninjinka!
You tasted like puke! Now you're
saw dust!
Yes!
[Gosoukan] We've been saved.
Huh? Where am I?!
And why is it snowing all
these crystals?
[Gosoukan] We are
eternally grateful.
We shall be more wary of our
offerings from now on.
[Chinpu] You have done so much
for us.
[Mingetsu] How can we show you
our thanks?
[Goku] You don't need to thank
us, but got any food?
Perhaps this will meet
your approval.
That'sll do.
Let's move.
Sure thing!
[Goku] Hey, Sanzo.
[Sanzo] What is it?
I'm sorry.
[Sanzo] Sorry? What for?
I'm sorry I'm such an idiot.
[Sanzo] Don't let that bother
you. You're in good company.
Got that right.
We wouldn't be going on
this journey
unless we were all a bunch
of idiots.
[Goku] What the heck is up
with Gojyo?
Why's he hanging around such a
little girl?
He sure is picking them young
these days.
He seems like the type who
tends to look after people,
then again maybe he's just
gotten himself into trouble.
So what else is new.
"Sweet Child of Mine."
Next time on Saiyuki.