[Goku] I'm hot!
[Gojyo] Shut up, you
stupid monkey!
Your hot air ain't making
it any cooler around here!
[Goku] Your overgrown hair
is far more obnoxious,
you carrot head!
Why don't you cut
that stuff off?
[Gojyu] You say that to my face.
[Sanzo] Hakkai, how much further
before the next town?
[Hakkai] According to the map,
we should come up on the village
of Tofugai any minute now.
[Goku] Hakkai, if we don't get
the pervy water sprite into
town, he's going to dry up.
[Hakkai] I'm afraid
we're out of water.
[Goyjo] Yeah, yeah. We had
this conversation yesterday.
[Hakkai gasp]
What, did a cat jump in front of
the jeep or something?!
Maybe you should get that other
eye checked out as well, huh?!
[Gojyo & Goku] Huh?
[Gojyo] A woman. And she's...
[Hakkai] She's a demon.
Please, I beg you...
You must take me to
the desert town of...
Tofugai.
[Goku] "Eternal Paradise"
[Gojyo] Here we are saving some
demon we hardly even know.
Sometimes I just don't
get what goes on in that
thick monk head of his.
Why not? We were all headed on
our way into Tofugai anyway.
[Gojyo] That's not the point!
Are you absolutely sure
about this, Sanzo?
I do not sense any evil or
hostility from that woman.
We'll just have to take her
with us to Tofugai and then
see what happens to her there.
Yeah... What could be
the harm in that?
[Goku] Wow, what is this place?!
My town of Tofugai will
be found at the very
bottom of this gorge.
You were... awake all along?
In return for saving my life,
I am offering my services
as your guide.
Let's go.
[All] Huh?!
Pardon me, but Sanzo...
Hakuryu is unable to fly
in his current form.
And it's a long way
down this gorge.
[Sanzo] Who asked him to fly?
I just want him to go down.
Okay, I guess I have
no choice then.
Hakkai, don't you dare even
think about doing it!
Everyone hold on!
Don't fail me, Hakuryu!
Oh my god! It's completely
dark down there! I can't
see a single thing!
This mist...
Hakkai, you bastard!
Don't you ever pull
a stunt like that again!
This mist... is as
thick as pudding.
Wha's up with this place?
I don't know.
Woman, where did you lead us?
[Goku] What?
[Gojyo] Earthquake?
[Kouran] This town is on the
verge of being swallowed up.
[Sanzo] Swallowed up? By what?
[Kouran] I do not know.
I am only your guide.
Please wait here while
I open the gates for you.
[Kouran] Once I have
opened the gates, please
go to the tower.
I will wait for you there.
Don't be late.
Who's bright idea... was this?
We can't go back now. Whatever's
going to happen, will happen.
And all this time I thought he
was saving her out of some sense
of mercy and compassion,
but now it turns out that he-
Hey! Those things are
for smacking people with,
not for throwing!
Where's that light coming from?
I can't say, but I sense
no danger or evil from it.
[Hakkai] In that case,
shall we go?
[Ni] Lady Koushu, how are you?
I trust you're in
excellent health?
[Koushu] Nevermind the
formalities just tell me
why you're here. I'm busy.
[Ni] A thousand pardons,
my lady. I shall deliver
my report right away then.
Did you tell her?
I'm afraid Lady Koushu is
extremely busy at the moment.
She does not wish to be bothered
about some insignificant
town in the desert.
[Huang] "Insignificant"?!
Tofugai is running with demons
that have managed to maintain
their sense of self.
[Huang] That added to the fact-
[Ni] Temper, temper.
Getting angry will only
irritate your skin, on top
of which, you'll have pimples.
Don't you mock me!
Need I remind you that
a particular party will
pass by that town?
[Ni] It appears that our
dear Lady Koushu simply cannot
be interested in such a
localized little village.
You wouldn't be suggesting that
you disapprove of the Lady's
inclinations, would you?
[Ni] Doctor Huang,
you aren't considering
offering counsel yourself?
[Huang] I'm going
to the bathroom!
[Ni] Ah, down the hallway
to your left, on the
right-hand side.
I know that!
[Goku] I don't see
a soul anywhere.
It's like a... a ghost town.
Huh?
[Goku] Sanzo, look!
Is everyone who lives in this
town a sculptor or what?
What awful taste!
I suggest we turn back now.
[Sanzo] It seems we have no
choice but to go by foot.
Gentlemen. These are no ordinary
statues we have here.
Oh? What exactly
are you sensing?
These statues must be
what became of the
town's inhabitants.
It's possible they turned
themselves into stone
for some reason.
Or maybe they were petrified
by someone else. But there is
something living inside them.
Sanzo...
Okay. That was weird.
[Sanzo] Let's head
for the tower.
That woman knows what's
going on here.
[Goyjo] Where the hell
are you, lady?
We came here, just like
you told us to
[Sanzo] Come out here!
Show yourself!
[Kouran] Sanz. I must insist
that you not kill anymore
of our townspeople.
Come again?
[Kouran] They are weak
and unable to withstand
your energies.
You must not touch.
I want to know the
meaning of all this?
What is your purpose
for bringing here?
[Kouran] To test you.
A test?
[Kouran] I shall reveal
all to the chosen ones
who can complete the trial.
Aw shucks. Flattery'll
get you nowhere.
[High pitched sound begins]
My ears!
What's wrong?!
[Goku] I don't know!
I'm turning into a statue!
This isn't funny!
Sanzo, it's a trap!
Get out of here!
I'm coming!
Wait. If I touch them, they
might disintegrate also.
She lured us here so that
she could snare us like
the rest of them.
You've got some nerve.
So, you finally show yourself?
[Kouran] Now I know the true
nature of your friends.
It looks like you're the
only one who was immune
to the petrification.
This is no concern of
yours. Now turn them back.
I have no time for
your stupid games!
The name I go by is Kouran.
This is all in accordance
with Master Wuhan's wishes.
[Kouran] It is said, "one day
four holy men will arrive.
If they be demon, they will
turn to stone in the city.
If they be human, they
will surely help us."
This is Master Wuhan's prophecy.
Wu-Wuhan?
Accordig to Master Wuhan's
will, I was to bring these
four holy men here.
Perhaps I was mistaken. You
are not the four I seek.
[Kouran] Such villainous...
[Sanzo] You dumb slut.
You're not getting away!
What is that woman up to?
Who are these people?
What a minute. What's
going on here?
They can see the energy
within you too.
[Sanzo] Explain.
[Kouran] The energy of the
chosen is so strong that
it would even be able to destroy
the demons living here.
[Sanzo] The chosen one? Energy?
What are you talking about?
[Kouran] You are chosen,
selected by Master Wuhan.
[Sanzo] Who is this Master
Wuhan?
[Kouran] Master Wuhan was
everything to us.
His prophecies brought us wealth
and allowed us to live in peace
until that fateful day.
The day the mist descended
on the gorge. Our fellow
townspeople working
the fields were suddenly
overcome by a murderous
rage and attacked us.
[Sanzo] The aura that rules
demons blanketing all of
Shangri-la...
Someone is attempting to
use the mist to try to
resurrect the Gyumaoh.
[Kouran] You are fighting
the people responsible
for this madness?
I'm just... on a
fieldtrip westward.
Is that the case? Won't
you please come and speak
with my Master Wuhan,
so that you may help us
save this town.
So I finally get to meet
the man himself, huh?
[Sanzo] There's one thing I
still don't understand.
And what might that be?
You're a demon just like
the others,
so how is it you were able
to keep your sanity when
the others weren't?
I wear special vestments
that can protect me from
the aura,
made by Master Wuhan himself.
It was only Master Wuhan's
holy powers, that allowed
this town of Tofugai to
remain a Paradise on Earth.
He bestowed these vestments
upon me and evacuated the
children and elderly.
[Sanzo] Wrong. The aura that
controls demons was probably
just slow to reach this place.
Wuhan had nothing to do with it.
[Kouran] Master Wuhan forsaw
that a savior would one day
arrive in this land.
Those who've been turned
into stone have been waiting
a long time for that day.
[Sanzo] How arbitrary.
He used magic to turn those
inconvenient to him into stone,
and rule over the helpless
with threats.
How dare you say that?!
Master Wuhan is absolute!
Even now, he's devoting
his ti-
Take a look and see what's
in their hearts!
Robbed of their freedom,
they'll go insane, and
suffer for eternity!
That is...
That is certainly not the
outcome that Master Wuhan
had intended for us.
The only thing he wishes is to
provide for peace in this town.
A peace he only keeps
by force. Pshaw.
[Kouran] Master Wuhan, I have
brought the man called Sanzo.
Please Master, I want
you to wake up.
A mummified monk? He died
while meditating, preserving
him instantly.
What in the world...
[Wuhan] Sanzo, it is
good of you to come.
You may call me Wuhan.
I protect the town of Tofugai,
and and make sure the people
go down the right path.
[Sanzo] Heh, funny. You
just look like some ole
dead geezer to me.
What's would some old fossil
want with a monk like me?
[Wuhan] There's no time.
Soon, the effects of my spell
will wear off,
and the town will collapse.
Then the demons will...
Hmph.
[Wuhan] Won't you protect
my town? Surely
it means something that you
appeared in my final moments.
That can't be a coincidence.
You say this is your town?
It's your town?
Just who in the hell do you
think you're talking to, sir?
I bet you feel like a saint
taking pity on these poor,
helpless townspeople even
after you're dead.
[Wuhan] You refuse to fight
because you believe
the one ruling the demons
is an unforgiving tyrant?
You're the one ruling the
people of this town!
[Wuhan] You are our only hope.
What you're doing is just
for your own satisfaction!
Don't blame others!
Wake up! This place
is falling apart!
Master... Wuhan...
[Huang] Doctor Ni. Tofugai
is being... swallowed up.
I told you, didn't I?
All we had to do was wait.
I won't go! I must stay here and
protect Master Wuhan from bein-!
Now wake up. Will you forget
about that old mummy's
elaborate speeches and take
a look around you?
It's collapsing! We have
to get out!
No we can't! If we leave then
they'll all turn into stone!
Into stone?! Try again!
What's waiting them is far
more terrifying of a fate!
It's much, much worse!
This is...
[Sanzo] This is what's happening
to Shangri-la right now.
Everyone, listen to me!
Have you forgotten
Wuhan's will?!
[fighting beginning]
Now stop this! We are
fellow townspeople!
Are you still not see what's
happening to these people?
They are only capable of seeing
us as beings to be destoryed.
Kouran...
Sanzo, we will continue living.
But we can not continue living
in the world as it is now.
We will wait for the day when
peace will return to us.
Do what you want.
But you better return here
as my companions.
[Kouran] Those who choose
to live, gather round.
We don't know when, but one
day we will be resurrected!
[Townspeople mumbling] I want
to live! I don't want to die!
O Tofugai, I seal thee!
[Kouran] Sanzo, thank you
for showing me the truth.
Peace... within a
tiny glass globe.
[Goku] I'm hot!
[Gojyo] Shut up, you
stupid monkey!
Your hot air ain't making
it any cooler around here!
[Goku] Your overgrown hair
is far more obnoxious,
you carrot head!
Why don't you cut
that stuff off?
[Gojyo] You say that to my face!
[Goku] Hakkai, how much further
before this town?
[Hakkai] According to the map,
we should come up on the village
of Tofugai any minute now.
Hakkai, if we don't get
this pervy water sprite
to town soon,he's going
to dry up and blow away.
I'm afraid we're out of water.
Yeah, yeah, we had this
conversation yesterday,
didn't we?
[All three] Huh?
Hold on, didn't we have
this conversation the day
before yesterday too?
Hey, Sanzo?
[Gojyo] Shut up, you
stupid monkey!
Hey, don't call me stupid!
[Gojyo] Stop shouting! You're
just making it hotter, dumbass!
[Goku] For a water sprite,
you're not so cool yourself!
[Gojyo] Eat my banana, monkey!
That'll cool you off.
[Goku] That's it! C'mon! We'll
settle this once and for all!
[Sanzo] Shut up, or I'll turn
you all into stone!
[All three] Huh?!
[Goku] Yaone's been captured
by a Special Anti-Demon Unit.
A bounty-hunting team that
specializes in killing demons.
We have to save her!
But if we go rescue Yaone,
we might have to fight an old
friend of Gojyo and Hakkai, who
just joined the bounty hunters.
Well that should make
things interesting.
Found out what happens in,
"The Truth of Justice"
Next time on Saiyuki!