Where the hell did you guys
come from?!
This is getting old fast!
Hey, what is this? Kill 1 demon
fight 4 more for free?
I'm still waiting for my prize.
After all, we've been at it for
three days!
Somebody out there must be
selling demons by the dozen.
And you know there's not a
single looker in the bunch.
Hey, don't these give-a-ways
usually have free food?
If that's the case then this is
turning out to be an All-You-Can
-Eat Buffet
Now that's my kind of sale!
I know, but it's a little much,
even for you.
Okay, it looks like we each take
about ten a piece.
Well let's go!
[Koushu] Why is it taking so
long to kill these rodents?
Well? Out with it.
You don't get it do you?
Right now they're fighting
reanimated corpses controlled
by demonic powers.
They're wasting their energy
and I'm wearing them down.
[Koushu] Just tell me when you
have the scripture.
Scripture?
Yes, scripture.
"The Death Sear"
Notice anything strange about
these guys?
You mean the fact that everytime
we kill them, they come back to
life like zombies?
By the power of the scripture...
the dead be gone!
[Goku] Boy I gotta get me one
of those.
Defeating those demonic nitwits
is nothing for a scripture of
this power.
[Koushu] I need that scripture.
Our need grows more dire by
the minute.
How so?
[Koushu] Surely you understand
the importance
of the Seiten Scripture. Or have
I forgotten to tell you?
It was used by the gods when
they created this world.
One of the founding scriptures
of Heaven and the Earth.
It governs the evolution of all
life. Everything.
So your point would be?
[Koushu] So impatient.
Somehow I thought you'd enjoy
our conversations more.
Enough with the chit-chat.
Get on with it.
Pay attention, this
is important.
The guardian of each one of
these five founding scriptures
is given the title of
Sanzo Priest.
Sanzo?!
So the little bastard is
a priest.
And our very esteemed
researcher, Doctor Ni,
has just made a
startling discovery.
Doctor Ni, join us.
[Ni] Why thank you. Lord
Kougaiji, I must say you're
exactly the way I pictured you.
But enough with the
pleasentries, I believe my
presence has been requested
to elaborate on procedures
regarding Lady Koushu's lover.
[Ni] Oh. Oh yes, he's also
your father, isn't he?
[Ni chuckles darkly]
So sorry. At any rate, with the
Seiten Scripture in hand,
all we need to revive Lord
Gyumaoh is obtain the Maten
Scripture, Genjo Sanzo
is carrying.
[Koukaiji] So all I have to do
is get the Maten Scripture,
and then the great Gyumaoh can
finally be awakened?
[Koushu] And then your mother
will be freed. That's what you
really want to know, isn't it?
That's right.
Why don't you ask me again when
you have the scripture in
your possesion?
Oh, that really pisses me off!
And I don't care if she is
my real mother!
Hey, getting ahold of one of
those scrolls or whatever is
she calls them,
Would sure teach that greedy
bitch a lesson.
[Sanzo] Shall we go?
Okay, somebody had to be
manipulating these guys
Could it be Kougaiji?
Perhaps.
[Goku] Hey, Sanzo.
You know that vest you're
always wearing?
What are you talking about?
He means the Maten Scripture.
Um, yeah! If you don't mind me
saying so,
that scripture kicked some
serious ass.
All those zombies in one
shot? Whoa!
[Sanzo] Yes, Goku.
[Sanbutsushin B] The sudden
rise of the demons that is
wreaking havoc across the globe
can only be caused by the
combining of science and
black magic.
Whoever is trying to revive
Gyumaoh has created a negative
energy that has spread
throughout Shangri-la.
And now, it is eating
away at this world.
I command you to find out who is
behind the revival of Gyumaoh,
and stop them before they have
brought destruction to
this world.
Do you understand?
The evil demon that devoured
humans whenever it pleased him
until the war god, Crown
Prince Nataku,
imprisoned him in Houtou Castle
centuries ago.
Gyumaoh!
The disturbance is in India!
Head west, and all is answered!
As you wish.
[Sanbutsushin C] Be forewarned
We sense that your master's
keep sake, the Seiten Scripture,
is being used for
the resurection.
If they came into possession
of yours as well...
The Maten Scripture in my
possession has the ability
to shatter darkness.
The Seiten Scripture of my
master has power to
create light.
That night I descended from
the mountain,
when the was stolen in
the attack.
[Goku] Sanzo! Sanzo, take a
look at that!
All that zombie killing's made
me hungry.
[Gojyo] If we stop we might run
into more of them though.
[Goku] I'm starving!
[Gojyo] Tough shit.
Look I'm so hungry I'll eat you
if we don't get a burger now!
You're damn right you can eat
me, you little twisted
monkey faggot!
You're the one with the
girly hair!
[Goku and Gojyo keep fighting]
When they get like this I
usually just like to go to my
own happy place.
[Goku and Gojyo keep fighting]
Are you really able to tune
them out?
[Goku and Gojyo keep fighting]
Hmmm. Nope.
[Koushu] Dealing with people who
are in no position to make
demands would be comical.
If it didn't piss me off
so much.
If I may be so bold as to say
so, it's not everyday you
run into someone willing
to destroy the world for their
own personal gain.
Doctor, is that supposed to be
a compliment?
Well if you don't like that one,
I could come up with another.
Hold it right there!
[Koushu] I will return your
mother to you as we agreed.
But remember...
Your father Gyumaoh belongs
to me.
He is to become his
formal husband.
I believe I've made
myself clear?
Yes, I beleive I have.
Oh Mother, I could probably
defeat even Sanzo and
his group.
But during our first
encounter...
I knew there was something
different about them.
But why do I hesitate?
Is it simply fear?
That's right! Could it be
true? Somehow in my heart
of hearts,
I know just how futile this
battle is!
Nothing is going to change even
if I'm able to defeat them.
But I promise you this, I will
save you, darling Mother!
Even if it means the destruction
of this world.
I will do everything within my
power to bring you back to life.
Even if it means sending
everything into chaos!
My Lord! Lirin's gone!
I looked everywhere in the
castle and I can't find
her anywhere!
How strange.
Hey I don't suppose you guys
have any idea
who might have stolen a flying
dragon, do you?
She didn't steal a dragon.
Did she?
That bitch!
What was she thinking?!
[Goku] Wow! Do you know how
long it's been since we've
been shopping?
[Gojyo] I'm actually relaxed.
[Sanzo] Good.
I'd forgoten what it was like
without demons around causing
trouble.
Wooooow! They're beautiful!
Hey Sanzo, I want you to buy be
some of these!
[Sanzo] Nu-uh.
[Goku] Why not?!
[Sanzo] Not listening.
[Goku] I'm not fasting!
Ah just give the kid a meat
bun, will ya?
Brats only whine because they
know you'll give them what
they want.
My, my, my look at how quickly
the droopy eyed priest has
become the mother around here.
Want to say that again?
[Chin] Excuse me gentlemen
over here.
You are all travelers, yes?
Come here, sit and I will tell
you what awaits you on
your journey.
[Gojyo] Heh, we've got no time
to listen to you and your
fortunes, buddy.
[Goku] Please, Sanzo!
Can't I have one little bun?
One little bun!
Shut up!
[Chin laughs]
Tell me now, do you know how
closely you walk with death?
Hey, mind your own business.
[Chin] Yes yes, no need to
answer. I see it in your face.
[Sanzo] Who are you?
[Chin] eath walks especially,
with you.
You can deceive the others with
those pretty boy looks,
but I can see the darkness
behind those eyes.
Sins beyond atonement!
And a scar, yes, a scar on
your belly.
You freak! You're just a
con artist!
Why young sir, I only say
this out of concern for
you gentlemen.
Who am I but just a silly man
who likes to tell fortunes?
Perhaps you would prefer to look
at my mah-jongg pieces.
Mah-jongg pieces?
[Chin] Yes, my pieces tell
people's fates. See?
Things do not look good for you.
Hey, how'd you do that?!
[Explosion]
What the?!
What the hell is that?!
Well Goku, looks like you got
your wish. That there's one hell
of a meat bun.
Looks a littel tough to me.
You try.
Hey guys, take a look at its
breast plate.
It's Sanskrit.
It looks like a shikigami.
He's right, that means it was
created by using black magic
to seal an evil script inside
its chest.
Whatever it is, it hardly seems
fair to send something that big.
It's just inhuman.
That man...
But I can see the darkness
behind those eyes.
Sins beyond atonement!
This shikigami could be one
of his.
[Sanzo] Is he one of Kougaiji's
assassins?
Something doesn't fit.
Boy he doesn't hold back.
Whatever should we do?
What we always do!
Kick its ass!
I don't know if any of you guys
are hungry but I'm gonna serve
up some...
...crab stew!
When are these gonna learn?
Don't mess with me when
I'm shopping!
[Koujaiji] I can't believe she
just left it sitting here.
[Yaone] That's not like her, she
must be close by.
When I get my hands on her...
What's with the act? We all know
that you're worried about her.
Huh, big brother?
No... What is this? I don't need
to listen to this crap.
Some of us have families.
[Doku] Stop being so sensitive.
I understand more than
you know.
My old man had a mistress too.
And he gave me a kid brother.
But by a different mother.
But he was dear to me, as much
of a brat as he was.
My mother suffered terribly.
But in the end I couldn't
save her.
Yes, I see a lot of me in
you, Koukaiji.
[Koukaiji] I'm sorry,
I didn't know.
Don't sweat it, man.
I'm not looking for sympathy.
I have my reasons for
being here.
What reasons?
When I came to the castle that
day you had no idea who I was,
but you took me without any
questions asked.
And that's when I vowed to
dedicate my life to serving you.
I understand.
You listen to me, my friend.
I'm with you because you always
follow your own path.
And wherever that road may take
you I promise we will be there.
You are our one true
lord, Koukaiji.
We won't let you down.
Alright! Who wants a piece
of me?!
Listen to me you bunch of
do-gooders, prepar to meet
your doom!
I'm not really up for this, why
don't you guys take her?
Maybe we should just ignore her.
Hey, Hakkai, doesn't she kind
of remind you of somebody
that we know?
You know, she is a little
like Goku.
Goku, you go play with her.
Aw!
Damnit! You guys aren't taking
me seriously!
I'm not a little girl!
Let me down! Let me down!
[Sanzo] Shut up and eat.
Okay!
Oh my. He sure is good a
taming wild animals.
[Koukaiji] Put her down!
What?!
[Kougaiji] Well if it
isn't Sanzo.
[Sanzo] Kougaiji.
You hand over my little sister,
right now!
Please come down and take her,
by all means.
Hi there! It's good to see ya!
You idiot! Get ass up here!
Oh, so you think you're getting
out of here that easily do ya?
[Goku] I'm waiting!
Be right there.
That's better! Let's finish what
we started the last time!
Hello.
What's up?
I was wondering, if you're not
doing anything,
would you consider maybe being
my oppenent? If you want to.
[Hakkai] Why, I would
be honored.
[Hakkai and Yaone fighting]
So it looks like it's just you
and me, Shoulder Pad.
[Doku] Gojyo?
Huh, it is you.
You know I wasn't 100% sure
until I saw you face to face.
It can't be...
Yeah.
It is you, Brother.
But why did you come back after
all this time, huh?
Sorry for the late introduction.
But I'm afraid I've give my
alliegence to Kougaiji.
And once I've made a promise.
No man, enemy or brother, can
ever make me break it.
Well that's too bad...
...because I don't break
them either!
Turn around, genius!
Why you arrogant little nimph!
Nailed him.
[Goku] Not quite, pixie!
He's only gotten stronger.
But so have I.
[Goku] Ready for more?
[Kougaiji] Well what have
we here?
That was quite a move you
had there.
Got anymore?
Aw, that's nothing!
Watch this!
You got it.
[Goku] If you want to take me
on, you can't be distracted
thinking about who you're
fighting for,
or what you're protecting. The
only way to have the strength
to defeat me is if you fight
for yourself!
Hear that, Kougaiji? You're
going to need all the help
you can get.
"Fight Party," on the
next Saiyuki.