[Nataku groans in
pain and coughs]
[Shien] Well fought,
Prince Nataku.
It's time to go home now.
[Nataku] Leave me alone!
I wanna see this...
just a little longer.
[Shien] But why?
[Nataku] I wanna stay here!
I'll be fine!
Just leave me be!
[Shien] What did you see
that day, Lord Nataku?
What did you see?
[Goku] "Ugly beautiful."
[Gojyo] Hey, leggo my egg roll.
[Goku] Ooh, no, not today!
[Gojyo] This is human food.
Go find a banana or something.
[Goku] Why don't you find a
cucumber, water sprite?!
Oooh. Now you've
done it, primate.
Yeah well, they're both about
the right size to satisfy
a pervert like you.
You had better learn to heel,
monkey, or I will rub
your nose in it.
I'm just getting started,
but I think it's about
time we settle this.
[Gojyo] Let's finish it!
[Goku] Any time,
any place, fool!
[Gojyo] Uh...
[Hakuyru squeaks happily]
[The patrons laugh]
It's so peaceful.
Hmph. It's about time.
No, not them.
I meant the village, Sanzo.
Hm?
I couldn't help but notice
it when we arrived in town.
It's nice to finally find
a place where we haven't
run into any demons.
Everyone's so lively.
Bet they're gearing up for
some kind of celebration.
[Waitress] I'm so sorry. I
thought you guys knew about it.
[Hakkai] Huh?
I just assumed you guys came
for the God Festival like
everybody else.
The God Festival?
Yep. Every year around
this time, a god descends
to the land of Saika.
[Hakkai] A god?
[Waitress] That's right.
It's what has kept the peace
here for all these years.
And today is the day we
have chosen to express our
gratitude to the heavens.
How cool!
A god is coming to town?
Have you ever seen
what he looks like?
Oh, come on.
You can't see a god.
I thought everybody knew that.
That's not true, I-
Ah! Of course we did!
What's this god's name?
His name?
Why it's Lord Shien, of course.
Shien?
[Waitress] I kinda like it.
[Zenon] Not that it's
any of my business,
but where were you off to?
Just out for some air.
I could use a little
bit of exercise.
[Zenon laughs]
Man, you're a terrible liar.
How long have I known you?
Five hundred years?
And every year
it's the same thing.
You go back on down there
to reminisce about Nataku.
And what for?
[Shien] Like I said.
I need the exercise.
Why do you insist on continuing
to sulk about it is beyond me.
It's not like it's your fault
Nataku ended up that way.
Get over it, man.
It's ancient history.
To be honest, I'm not
quite sure what is true
in this world anymore.
[Zenon] Huh?
What a caring young man.
It is Shien, isn't it?
Aw man. So it's not Homura?
As much as I don't like
having demons around,
gods bring their own set
of problems with them.
Regardless, there's no
reason to stick around.
[Hakkai] Yep. I'll feel better
as soon as we put some distance
between us and this place.
[Huang] Lirin?! Lirin!
[Huang] Where could that
brat have run off to?!
Did you lose something,
Dr. Huang?
[Huang] That little monster
took off in the middle
of my experiment!
What am I suppose to do now?!
I need that data!
No need to get your panties
all in a bunch over it.
Besides, I seem to recall you
were against experimenting
on our little princess.
But once the Lady has
given an order, I obey!
I was just upset
about my evaluation,
if it's any of your business.
Oh, you don't say?
[Huang growls]
Don't let him get to you.
[Huang] Lirin, you
can come out now!
I've got some candy!
Aye yi.
[Lirin] Is the coast clear?
Yes, you can come out now.
Yippie! I'm free at last!
You're welcome.
I swear, that woman is
so persistent, sheesh.
Agreed.
I still don't understand why
you helped me hide from her.
I wasn't doing anything.
And I'd thwart Ms. Huang even
if the Gyumaoh project
wasn't stalled.
[Lirin] Is that so?
[Ni] Yep.
I'm afraid the Seiten Scripture
has been stolen from us.
What?!
The Seiten Scripture
has been stolen?!
I'm sorry, I thought you knew.
I'm afraid our pompous
little prince picked a
fight with a god and lost.
And it cost us the scripture.
He beat my brother?
[Ni] You can't really blame
him. The Prince did fight
a god, after all.
But perhaps the
Princess could win.
This god fella, take me
to him and I'll show him!
Let's just do a quick little
search on gods, shall we?
Ooh! It looks like we know the
exact location of where a god
will be showing up today.
You do? Show me!
Saika, huh? You're toast, buddy!
[Ni] You show him, princess.
Teach that god who's boss,
so I can collect
some wonderful data.
[Sounds of Gyumaoh
and Nataku battling]
[Soldier 1] Lord Shien,
you have to let us attack!
[Soldier 2] Nataku can't
fight Gyumaoh on his own!
It's suicide!
I don't care if he is a war god!
Do you really intend
to just stand there?
I'm afraid I can't
allow you to engage.
Li Touten has given us strict
orders that this is to be
between Gyumaoh and Nataku.
But lord! For the soldiers
of the Heavenly Army to
just stand by and watch
as one of our own...
Is humiliating, isn't it?
I agree.
But I would not be so eager
to kill if I were you.
Are you really so eager to get
demon blood on your hands?
Now that the Emperor
has found his scapegoat,
perhaps you think wiping
them out will curry you
favor somehow.
But you'll gain nothing by
joining his crusade except
becoming an accomplice.
No, we shall wait here until
Nataku subdues Gyumaoh,
or dies trying.
[Birds chirp in the distance]
[Shien] Why Nataku preferred
this mundane scenery to the
perfection of heaven,
I'll never know.
After five hundred
years of coming here,
I have yet to see why.
So this is how I
pass the centuries,
practicing and honing
my skills so that I may
become an invaluable
servant to War Prince Homura.
By aiding this disobedience,
I suppose I have fooled myself
into believing I can atone
for becoming the tool for
Nataku's destruction.
I've found you, god!
[Lirin yells]
My goodness! You're too
powerful! I give up!
Stop playing around and get up.
Hehe, was I that obvious?
[Lirin] Hey you! Bad god guy!
Yeah you! You'll pay
for beating my brother!
Prepare to totally get your
ass kicked and hand over
the Seiten Scripture!
You're... Gyumaoh's
daughter, aren't you?
Hey! Stop running away!
[Shien] Run away?
The very idea...
This should be about far enough.
Very well. Shall we?
Hehe! Not nearly
far enough, mister!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, YEAH!
Nyah, nyah! You missed me!
[Shien] Of course I did. I stood
far enough back so you'd have
time to dodge my attack.
[Lirin yells]
[Lirin] That was just a
shockwave of his whip!
Better not get close
enough to see what the
real thing feels like.
I know. I'll do little
Lirin fireballs instead!
[Shien] A cute trick.
But a bit outside your
age group, don't you think?
It's about time you children
learned not to play with fire.
[Gojyo growls]
[Goku] What the hell, Hakkai?!
Huh?
[Hakkai] Miss Yaone?
Why, it's you.
You should be more careful.
Watch where you're going.
[Yaone] I'm sorry, but I'm
a little frantic right now.
I can't seem to
find Lirin anywhere.
Is she lost?
[Yaone] She snuck out
of the castle last night,
so I was hoping I might
find her here with you guys.
Have you seen her?
Yeah, Sanzo. Have YOU seen her?
Why are you asking me?
Well, she is your
play pal, isn't sh-
Please continue.
Mommy...
Where in the world could
she have run off to?
And you've seen absolutely
no sign of her?
Well, yes. I've found one
of the flying dragons nearby.
You don't think she...
It's Shien.
What?
[Loud explosion in the distance]
That looks like his
handiwork to me alright.
Oh, no! Lirin!
Wait! Yaone!
Whoa!
[Hakkai] We'll take you.
Dammit, Hakkai!
I know, I know.
But we can't just leave
her like this, can we?
Tch.
[Lirin] Die, will you!
[Shien] So I fight the daughter
of the demon I refused to
face so long ago.
Perhaps this was meant to be.
[Lirin gasp, then yells]
[Shien] You should know we
gods are very egalitarian.
We never discriminate.
Demons, women and children
all have a chance...
to join us or die,
however they see fit.
Tell me, which do you choose?
[Yaone] I'm coming, Lirin!
Not a wise choice.
[Lirin] Wow, Yaone. What are
you doing with the bald monk?
I thought they
were the bad guys?
Trust me, it's only temporary.
[Goku] What are we running for?
We can take him, easy.
[Gojyo] For once,
I agree with the monkey.
He's alone this time.
[Hakkai] We shouldn't run
headlong into battle with
a god, alone or not.
[Goku] But he's right there!
[Sanzo] Shut up and walk. We
get in enough fixes on our own.
[Gojyo] What the...?!
[Hakkai] Looks like Shien
found the trap that Yaone set.
Though I'm willing to bet it
didn't slow him down much.
[Yaone] No, but at least
we know where he is now.
Pretty close from
the looks of it.
I give up.
Hey, where do ya
think you're going?
[Hakkai] To see
if I can stall him.
You guys find a way out of here.
I'll catch up with you later.
I wanna go too!
The only one who's allowed
to beat you up is me.
So let me take 'em.
Listen, Hakkai...
Are you sure about this?
Yes. If Shien's after anything,
it's either Lirin or your
Maten Scripture, so...
[Hakuryu squeaks sadly]
[Hakkai] Please take
care of Hakuryu for me.
All right.
All right?! That's it?!
You're going to leave them?!
That's right. Let's go.
How can you just abandon your
friends like that? I swear!
Step aside!
[Sanzo growls]
[Lirin gasp]
[Sanzo] What a pain in the ass.
Master Sanzo, I know that you've
done an awful lot for me.
So I feel I should
tell you next time...
I will be forced to take the
Maten Scripture from you.
[Sanzo] Hmph.
[Yaone] Please take good
care of Lirin for me.
[Sanzo] I'm dumping
her outside the forest.
Thanks. That's all I ask.
[Shien] My...
Three demons against me.
No. Make that four.
[Hakkai] Yaone!
[Yaone] Don't mind if I
crash the boys club, do you?
[Hakkai] But...
[Yaone] Well, do you?
[Gojyo] What the hell.
I'm always looking for
some female companionship.
I guess it's your choice.
Do you mind?
To be honest, it's not my habit
to gang up on someone like this.
It's quite alright.
I don't mind.
I should tell you, I think
we have the better hand, chump.
He said it's fine. Let's go!
That's true.
It looks like I'll get that
work out I was looking for.
Stand back!
Got him?
[Shien] Tenpou...
[Gojyo] Hakkai!
[Goku, growling] You're mine!
Son Goku...
[Goku] Can't tie me up!
[Shien] I see your
skills are improving.
[Shien chuckles]
Huh?!
[Shien] Thanks for the work out.
I shall keep you in mind for
the next time I'm in need
of a good sparring partner.
What the hell?!
We just got started!
Get yer butt back heeere!
[Nataku] But Shien,
I promised to show him
around the Heavens as soon
as my wounds were healed!
I have to!
[Shien] Prince Nataku,
who are you referring to?
[Nataku] I don't know.
He said he didn't have a name.
[Shien] Prince Nataku,
perhaps one day I too
will be able to see
what you saw in that place.
[Footsteps approaching]
[Homura] How'd it go?
[Shien] Actually, it
was quite productive.
[Zenon] Are those your whips?
Did Goku do this?!
He did.
I think it's time, don't you?
[Homura] It certainly
appears that way.
[Lirin] I got it!
It's mine, it's mine!
[Yaone] Lirin, stop it!
You're acting like a child!
[Lirin] Yippie! Yippie! Yippie!
She got you good, Sanzo.
[Lirin] Heh!
[Goku] Hey!
[Sanzo] Tell me... why
is this brat still around?
[Goku and Lirin argue]
[Hakkai] Put down the gun.
Since we were here,
I figured that maybe
we would enjoy the festival.
[Goku] Give it back!
[Hakki] Now that
I've faced him...
I understand him so much better.
I've never fought anyone
with such utter conviction
and determination.
You know, I know
exactly what you mean.
His strength is entirely
different from Homura's
or Zenon's on a strictly
fundamental level.
If that's true then...
he may be plagued
with self doubt or
questioning his purpose,
if you know what I mean.
If you probe deeply enough,
you'll find most tough guys
are all the same way.
[Hakkai] You really think so?
You're telling me you don't
sense it in yourselves?
Inside your heart of hearts,
you're plagued with doubt
and uncertainty,
so you fight to feel like you
have control of your own lives.
Because in the struggle,
you can find your purpose.
Hmph. Maybe so.
That goes for you to, I suppose.
You ate it all, didn't you?!
You're gonna pay for this!
[Lirin] Yum, yum! Hehe!
[Goku] You're so dead!
Do you think those gods
stand a chance against
such insecure guys?
Probably not.
[Goku] Get back here!
[Lirin laughs]
He he. Look here, Snoogums.
What interesting data we have.