[Jiroushin] Pardon me, Goddess,
but why did you send the choosen
four on an earthbound path?
Their journey west would be far
faster if you would have allowed
them Heavenly travel.
[Merciful] Geographical
arrival's not the only goal.
Currently, they are painfully
lacking in both the ability
and the solidarity
that will be necessary for them
to accomplish our true goal.
They're not only traveling to a
physical destination but a
spiritual one as well.
Of course. I'm sorry, I should
not have doubted your methods.
I'm kidding. It's just that it's
so much more interesting this
way. Don't you think?
[Goku] 996...
997, 998, 999...
One thousand!
That's it I'm done!
Time to throw 'em down and have
one of you guys pick up
the pack!
[Everyone] One, two, three...
This is bullshit! Next time
we're gonna draw straws or
something like that!
He'll be carrying that pack all
the way to India.
He always throws down scissors.
You'd think he'd catch on
by now.
Pick it up, let's go.
Ugh, how much farther do we have
to walk?!
[Hakkai] As long as the path is
impassable by jeep.
God you suck! I know you can
turn into something other than
a jeep!
You just don't want to give us
a ride!
Sanzo, I believe it's time to
put your animal and Hakkai's
animal in seperate cages.
At this break neck pace it
doesn't look like we're going
to get past the mountain range
by sunset.
All right, then. I suggest
accommodations at this humble
little establishment.
Aw man!
Now this is my kind of humble
little establishment.
Excuse me!
What is it that you want?
[Hakkai] We're traveling west
and it grows dark.
We humbly request accomedations
for the night.
This is a sacred temple, and
none but the holy and
the blessed
may enter this door way or
reside within these walls.
Shit! What the hell's up
with that?!
Monks! They're all religious
hypocrites too busy praying to
practice what they preach!
[Sanzo] Watch your mouth.
[Hakkai] Yeah. Hold it down.
Man! I'm hungry do something
Sanzo!
By the goddess, he said Sanzo!
[Monk A] Yes, he wears the robes
of the late Koumyou Sanzo.
The Founding Scripture of
Heaven and Earth they adorn
his shoulders.
The crimson chakra upon his
brow, the mark of one close
to the gods.
Forgive us, Genjo Sanzo!
Sanzo! I will go and tell the
others he's here!
I will be right down to let
you inside!
Priest Sanzo, you honor this
old temple with your presence.
You will be extended
every courtesy.
We are grateful for
your welcome.
Okay, so just how much of
a big shot is he anyway?
Sanzo isn't his name, Gojyo,
it's more a title he's
been given.
There are five sacred scriptures
in the world called the Founding
of Heaven and Earth,
and if I've got this right, the
title of Sanzo is one given to
the guardians of each of
these scriptures.
Among those who hold to the
tenents of the Buddhist faith,
they are revered as the most
holy of all monks.
So the entire baldy
consortium has no clue
he's a complete dickhead.
They're putting us up for the
night. Shut up.
[Abbot] You know, Priest
Koumyou Sanzo
also graced this temple with
his presence almost thirteen
years ago.
His majesty was second only to
his humility.
His presence is still fresh in
my memory.
If I may say so, you greatly
resemble Master Koumyou.
I heard news of Master
Koumyou's passing,
shortly there after I learned
that his favorite student,
had taken up his mantle, I am
pleased for you. Proud of you.
Your praise is appreciated. It
would be too dangerous to pass
these mountains in the dark,
so we are grateful you are
allowing us to stay the night.
We would be happy to allow you
to stay, it's just...
Just what?
It's just that this temple
is sacred,
and our order does not allow
outsiders to pass through
our doors.
And these three gentlemen over
there hardly seem to be either
devout or contrite.
You'll let the monk stay, but
you're going to let us sleep
outside on the rocks?!
I wouldn't stay here if you got
on your knees and begged me!
[Hakkai] Speak for yourself.
You can sleep where you want.
I don't want to sleep on
the rocks.
Remember that these monks are of
a very devout order, Gojyo.
Yeah the order of
judgmental assholes.
[Monk C] Are they your pupils
Genjo Sanzo?
[Sanzo] No.
They're my servants.
[Gojyo and Goku throw a fit
about being called servants]
You even think about touching my
plate, I'm going to cut your
hand off.
I'm hungry and you've
got plenty!
You try it, you die!
[Hakkai] Will you knock it off?
Man, those monks kick ass in
the kitchen!
And the accomedations aren't
that bad either.
My goodness, how will we ever
repay you for graciousness to
include us, your highness.
I'm going to kill you.
Have you found the room to
your liking?
My name is Yo, and I have
been given the high honor of
attending to all your needs.
Simply ask and I will provide
it for you.
Dude, I seriously doubt you
could provide for any of
my needs.
Not unless you got an
older sister.
You better watch your mouth!
Women are positively forbidden
in this temple.
Isn't that right, Master Sanzo?
Why are you doing this to me?
I have to confess, this is the
highest honor ever bestowed
upon me, Master Sanzo.
I've never met a holy man
chosen by Buddha himself!
It's men like you who are the
reason I've dedicated my life
to the Buddhist faith!
I cannot tell you what this
moment means to me!
I promise you, I will put my
heart and soul into making your
stay here a pleasant one!
If there is anything you need
at all, Don't hesitate to call
my name. Really!
You? A holy man!? Yeah right!
[mockingly] "I cannot tell you
what this means to me! Do not
hesitate to call my name!"
You know what this means,
don't you?
[All three] He doesn't know you
very well.
You guys, I'm still hungry!
And I've got gas like you
wouldn't believe, all these
vegetables and beans. Blech.
They're Buddhists so they're
vegetarians and if you think
about farting, I'll kill you.
His farts would almost be better
than all this nasty incense.
You can all put up with it for
one night.
Last piece... call.
Call, all triple straights.
What's going on? What are
you doing?!
[All four] It's Mah-jongg!
Damn it!
So you were waiting for the
"five of wan" tile.
[Yo] No drinking! No smoking!
We are confiscating all
of this!
Man...
Do not "man" me!
We are in a sacred temple!
Act like it!
I don't understand how none of
you seem to know anything about
the ways of the Buddha!
It's like each of you are asking
for Buddha's retribution to come
raining down on upon you!
Just go to bed.
[Goku] Sanzo, toss me the comics
when you're finished with the
paper, will ya?
[Sanzo] Yeah, sure man,
no sweat.
Aah! Are you guys even listening
to me?!
[All three] Uh no.
Tell me, has this temple
suffered from any unusual
demonic activity recently?
No, of course not.
It is said that by the Lord
Buddha's protection,
this temple is warded from such
worldly things.
Because our deep devotion has
been communicated to the
Lord Buddha.
Well what are you gonna do if
they do attack you? What then,
Mini Monk?
That would never happen in a
million years, but if it did
the Merciful Goddess would
protect us.
Right, but if she didn't you got
guns and shit right?
Of course we don't, killing goes
against everything Buddha
stands for.
Good god, kid, you're
killing me.
Then that's all the more reason
we should probably keep
the duration of our little visit
here short.
[Goku] Beef, pork,
chicken, fish.
[Gojyo] Women, liquor, smokes.
Okay, you both are
just pathetic.
Where's Sanzo?
Our little helper came and said
the Abbot wanted to see him.
This late at night?
What is it?
I think we've got company.
No way! Another assassin?!
We'll be lucky if it's just one.
Come out, come out where ever
you are, Genjo Sanzo!
I have orders from Lord
Kougaiji himself.
I have come to take your life!
Oh my, I do so love the taste of
tender monk flesh.
A demon!
To temple!
Do not panic!
Use the signs! Form the signs
and chant the scriptures!
By the power of the Merciful
Goddess be gone demon!
Your evil has no place in this
most holy of temple! Go!
Now you die!
We begin!
[Monks chanting]
He dies. It's working!
No, it's not!
Your chanting is just noise
to me!
You're pathetic!
Merciful Goddess please
save us! Please! Please!
Yes? Why did you call me here?
Though we do not know your
plans Genjo Sanzo,
we wish to ask you to consider
prolonging your stay here at
our temple.
I'm afraid my journey is
urgency makes that impossible.
[Priest B] For just a month,
please! A week at least! Sure
you can remain a week.
Your visititation to this place
is a sign we have been
searching for,
and surely you yourself can feel
the hand of the lord Buddah in
bringing you here.
It would be a great honor to
all of us if you would bless
us with your wise teaching,
Genjo Sanzo.
Perhaps not. Tell me, did you
ask the same request
of Koumyou Sanzo when he
came here?
We did, but disappointingly,
he did not comply with our
sincere request.
I have the feeling you would
not have liked his sermons as
much as you think.
[Priest B] Why would you
say that?
[Priest C] Of course we would!
Perhaps you would like me to
deliver the message that
Koumyou Sanzo
was too polite or forgiving
to give you?
That all of you are spoiled,
and frankly you're a bunch of
old farts. There.
How dare you address me
this way!
[Priest B] Yes! Y-You go
too far!
Great One, you must
come quickly!
A demon has entered the temple
and demands we surrender Genjo
Sanzo and his companions,
and he vows he will slay us all
until they are given to him!
[Sanzo] What?!
Come on, Genjo Sanzo!
I've had my fill of monks and
I'm ready to move on to
tastier fair!
Tell me child, do you have a
name selected? The one you will
take on in the after life?
[Gojyo] Damn, this is a big
let down.
I can't believe this is their
second try.
I mean they might have sucked
but at least their first go
around was pretty to look at.
I know you! You're the three
demons who have betrayed us!
I'm going to enjoy tearing the
three of you apart!
One at a time or all together!
Yes! I'll even let you decide
the order in which you all die!
[Axe Demon laughs]
So, what do you think, Goku?
Seems like an asshole and he's
got bad hair. I say -20 points.
Take off another 15. His clothes
are lame and he smells.
How dare you! How dare you
mock me!
Aw dude, bad teeth take off
another 5!
Bad aim, that's another 10.
No! They're fast!
This is impossible!
They are no ordinary demons!
Okay, that didn't take any time
at all!
Maybe this is just his way of
making us think he's got
us whipped
before he brings out the
big guns.
How very perceptive of you.
[Hakkai] Oh please.
Oh, he resists me!
[Goku] You're getting the hang
of this!
Yeah, I kinda thought of it
when taking out that little
spider lady the other day.
Materialize a little chi. Make a
barrier wall. Not bad, eh?
His powers are immense!
I was not told!
Awesome! Come on dude, hook me
up with a few tricks like that,
will ya?
You have to be able to
concentrate, and that's
not really your strong suit.
These demons still wear their
power limiters!
What would happen if they took
those chains of magic off?!
Let's find out!
Why don't I show my demon
brethren the true extent
of my powers?
So that's why his little
ensemble is missing the
right sleeve.
And I thought it was just a
really bad fashion statement.
And that will be the last
statement you'll ever make!
We'll see about that!
He's strong. Strong as
he smells.
And that's saying something,
coming from you.
You'll never win! So you can die
now or later.
And you're not all that bright
either. Take away another 45.
Nice shot!
With that many point he's
definitley out of the game.
You know, your penchant for
dramatic entrances is getting
kinda obvious.
I could've taken care him all by
myself, thank you very much.
Of this I'm sure.
If you're an example of the
caliber of assasins he's sending
this Lord Kougaiji of yours,
well he must painfully
underestimate our potential.
What is the real purpose of the
experiments to revive Gyumaoh?
Tell me who is behind all
of this?
You. You stink of human blood.
How many people's blood have you
been splattered with?
You shame your own faith!
For that, I'm taking another 20.
And that's it game over.
I don't think so.
I've got another hand!
By the powers of heaven...
Be gone!
You only get one
continue, buddy.
[Hakkai] So there you are!
Are you okay? Are you hurt.
Who- Who are you people?
I heard it say you've been
splattered by the blood of many!
If you've killed so many how are
you better than any demon?
[Goku] Look you stupid little
jerk, if we wouldn't have
stopped him
he would have eaten your happy
ass too.
[Hakkai] We don't want to kill,
but I'm afraid they leave us
little choice.
But you always have a choice!
The act of taking a life, no
matter whose live it is,
is blasphemy against the
teachings of the Lord Buddha!
Tell me, do you really believe
what you're saying?
Do you still mean that after
you've just seen the slaughter
of your own brothers?
If you want to be so close to
the gods so badly perhaps you
should join them.
Everyone becomes closer to
Buddha when they stop breathing.
It's harder to be close while
you still are.
You're right.
You're alive. Think about
that, kid.
We're all alive for a reason.
Find out why.
What is it?
Master, when you and your
friends come this way
after your journey is over,
would you come visit our
emple again?
Because I'd... Because I'd
really like you teach me
how to play mah-jongg, if you
would please.
I'd like that very much.
Bless them on their journey,
Lord Buddah. Bless them.
[Goku] Does the name Jien mean
anything to you? No? Well,
me neither.
But apparently to Gojyo and
this chick who really gets
off doing laundry
that name means a lot. What, you
ask? Hell, I don't know.
They don't tell me nothing
around here.
All I know is this need-to-know
basis for old Goku's getting on
my nerves!
[Gojyo] God, dude, quit
your whining.
[Goku] I'm not whining!
Stay tuned for "Crimson Tears."