[Homura taking deep breaths]
[Gojyo] This must be the place.
No doubt about it.
So that's the Tower of Konran.
So that's where I'll
find those gods, right?
Let's go!
So they're here.
[Goku] "Showdown at
the Tower of Konran."
[Shien] Destroying this world
to make way for a new one...
That is why I am here.
But still, I can't help but...
wonder if the universe we
create will be any better.
But it's useless
to second guess.
I made my choice
a long time ago...
and there's no deviating
from this path once
I've set upon it.
Yes, I chose to put all my
faith in Homura then...
when I saw the horrible
things we'd done to you,
in the name of Heaven.
Nataku... this life has
been so cruel to you.
You are the only one who
could stop us, if you had
not locked your heart away.
Once the weight of
the world is gone,
then maybe you can
open it up again.
We shall see.
At least in the next world,
there is hope.
It is time.
I'm ready for them.
Konzen Douji...
Field Marshal Tenpou...
General Kenren,
and Son Goku.
Have you not suffered
as we have?
Are your hearts not also
filled with sorrow?
Then, why do you oppose us?
Can't you see that the only way
to get rid of the pain...
is by destroying everything?
Break through the door, Hakkai!
I'm one step ahead of you,
Sanzo!
[Goku] Do it!
I'll say... one thing for ya!
You'll... make a big entrance!
You got that... right!
[Hakuryu squeaks]
[Hakkai] Funny.
I was expecting more
of a welcome than this.
[Gojyo] Not very good
hosts, are they?
It doesn't matter... whether
it is a trap or it isn't...
We have to get moving.
Got that right!
[Sanzo] Here they come now.
[Goku] I don't sense
Homura or the others.
Are you sure?
[Male voice] So good of
you to come, Genjo Sanzo.
I don't believe we've ever met.
[Male voice] I'm Gairu,
leader of the Holy Demon Army.
By Lord Homura's will,
I shall give you death.
No thank you. The only presents
I accept are from the ladies.
But I insist.
Believe me, it will
be no trouble at all.
I'm sick and tired of your
delusions of grandeur!
Why don't you try us again in
about ten billion years or so?
And, for your information,
I can be a giving
person as well!
[Sanzo] Stop wasting our time.
Our business is with Homura.
Step aside!
[Gairu] What if I don't want to?
[Sanzo] Then you die.
Get them!
[Demons growling and snarling]
It can't be!
It looks like I'm
running out... of time.
[Zenon] You look worried.
Is something wrong?
[Homura] No.
[Homura] They are curious
though, aren't they?
At first glance, they appear to
have nothing at all in common.
Yet they work together
in perfect harmony,
each one's strength making
up for the other's weakness.
Genjo Sanzo...
[Shien] Cho Hakkai...
[Zenon] Sha Gojyo...
[Homura] And...
Son Goku.
A creature born from
a rock on Mount Kaka.
Your individuality
makes you invincible.
A heretic with golden
eyes. He is the secret.
Son Goku must be captured.
[Shien gives a short chuckle]
This is exactly what we've been
preparing for all this time.
So, you need the monkey
to create a new Heaven
and Earth, is that it?
Well, you get the prize.
[Shien] The Holy Army is
reporting that Sanzo and party
have already breached the tower.
[Zenon] I have a feeling Goku
won't need any help finding us.
But, it won't do us any good if
he gets killed, now will it?
He's not much good to
us if he can't even get
this far, now is he?
Don't you worry. He'll be here.
I have no doubt.
[Homura] I have no doubt.
Son Goku, the only being
capable of seeing the
ephemerality of life.
I will possess you...
no matter what.
[Demon yells]
Heh. Somehow I was expecting
a little more from
Homura's minions.
No joke. Taking these guys
out was almost too easy.
Well then, it looks to me
like we're all done here.
[Sanzo] I guess...
that leaves you.
[Gairu] Oh, I beg to differ.
What?!
[Demons growling]
No way! They're dead!
Okay, I never expected this.
That's why they're so weak.
The benevolent Homura has
granted us, eternal life
and the very power of the gods!
I do hope you're not in a hurry.
This could take a while,
and we've got all
the time in the world!
[Gairu laughs triumphantly]
I never was the
very patient type.
[Hakkai] This could turn
out to be rather tedious.
[Homura] Behold, gentlemen.
The pentagram... with the power
to create Heaven and Earth.
The Maten Scripture occupies
this point of the star.
The Seiten Scripture occupies
the other.
As we take the place of the
three remaining scriptures,
the five points of
the star are completed.
[Shien] What incredible power.
Just look at it...
All that power resonating from
the five corner points is
collecting in the middle.
But it's not only
our powers collecting.
It feels like all the spiritual
power of the entire world...
is being transmitted through
us towards the center.
[Zenon] It's amazing, isn't it?
All we've done is
stand in our places.
[Shien] I can't
say I'm surprised.
We are talking about harnessing
enough energy to recreate the
universe, after all.
[Homura] But I'm afraid
it's still incomplete.
Only by placing Son Goku in
the center of the pentagram,
will we be able to conjure up
the power necessary to replace
Shangri-La with a new world.
He is the key.
[Homura] Hurry, Son Goku.
Come to claim...
your destiny!
[Gods panicking]
Reporting in! We are reading
an enormous power surge from
the Tower of Konran, my lord!
This smells like Homura's
deceitful treachery to me, sire.
His blasphemous scheme is
on a scale that could restart
creation, and form
a new Heaven and Earth.
But why?! Tell me why this fact
was not reported to me earlier!
An emergency summons!
Gather all the members of
the high council at once!
[Goddess] They're panicking
right on schedule. Heh.
That sure takes some of
the excitement out of it.
Merciful Goddess,
what are you doing here?!
Don't you know what's
happening down there?!
Isn't it obvious?
I just want to see...
what life brings their way.
[Jiroushin] What kind
of nonsense is that?
Can't you see how
serious this is?
We're talking about the complete
destruction of Heaven!
But of course.
Let me remind you, Jiroushin,
that of all the gods,
only I could see this coming
from a mile away.
And it doesn't BOTHER you?
This by-the-number script
was written for us long ago.
Why should I complain
about my part in it now?
That won't accomplish anything.
But... u-uh...
[Goddess] It was inevitable.
How foolish of us to think men
like that could waste away
in this prison forever.
[Goddess sighs]
I am just so envious.
Um, please forgive me...
Yes, I know.
They've called a meeting, right?
[Messenger God] Ah, yes.
[Goddess] Let's go, Jiroushin.
It's time to watch some gods
bicker endlessly as their
kingdom crumbles beneath them.
The things you say!
What am I going to do with you?!
[Goddess] I will
do my part, Konzen.
You just do what you do best.
Handle things in your own way.
[Demons yelling]
Hey, you say something?
No, nothing.
You'd better rest up, monk.
All this demon shooting
must be starting to really
affect your hearing.
You hear what I'm saying?
I'll shoot you.
You asshole! You could
have accidentally shot me!
Did you say something to me?
I must be hearing things.
CAN YA HEAR ME NOW, ya blonde,
himbo, wannabe bastard!
[Demons growling]
[Sanzo] What did you call me?
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
The demons?
Make me do all of the work!
What are we going
to do about them?!
Our usual methods don't seem
to be effective this time.
[Sanzo] We could chop them
up until they can't be
resurrected again.
[Hakkai] Or find a way to
vaporize them into molecules.
That's one way we could
buy us a little time.
That Homura...
sure is a cunning
bastard, all right!
[Homura] Just look
at it, Rinrei.
It's what we always wanted.
A place where we
can truly be free.
Out here, there is
no heresy or taboos.
And a love as pure as ours...
would never be forbidden.
Let us begin.
What is that?!
Look up there! Even from
all the way down here,
I can sense an
enormous flow of chi.
Just what in the hell
are those guys up to?
[Demons yell]
[Sanzo] I guess they weren't
joking when they said they
wanted to wreck the Heavens.
You're right. This isn't funny.
Looks to me like we better
kick things up a notch.
Right.
Pay attention!
We are coming for you!
[Demons growling]
[Both] Will you shut up?!
Why won't these guys ever learn?
It's going to hurt every
time we kill 'em.
It's like we're caught
in an endless loop, man!
Boy, you're a quick one.
Sanzo, I believe I may
have a way out of this.
I just need you to head
upstairs for a moment.
It shouldn't take too long.
[Both] Huh?!
Why didn't I think of that?
[Hakkai] You like it?
I came up with it myself.
[Sanzo] Are you
absolutely serious?
[Hakkai] I wasn't entirely
joking about it, no.
[Sanzo] Hakkai, you
aren't planning to...
Please, there's no time.
I know what I'm doing, Sanzo.
You just go on without me.
[Sanzo] I suppose there's
no talking you out of it.
Got that? You come with me.
We aren't going to just
leave him here, are we?
You nuts? What makes you
think you can do it alone?
Don't you worry.
I'll be more than enough
for them. Promise.
You're not actually going to...
Gojyo, Goku, trust
me on this, okay?
[Sanzo] Move out.
[Goku] Wait a minute!
Sanzo, you can't!
[Gojyo] Aaah, hell.
We'll do it your way this once.
[Hakkai chuckles]
Thanks. Oh, Gojyo!
Could you take care
of Hakuryu for me?
[Hakkai] I couldn't forgive
myself if he got hurt in here.
Don't die.
I don't plan to, believe me.
You can't leave!
Looks like I'm your
only opponent left.
If you want to stop them, you'll
have to get through me first.
[Goku] Maybe we should
go back and check on him.
[Sanzo] Will you be quiet?
[Goku] But Sanzo! He-
[Gojyo] There it is.
[Sanzo] After you.
[Goku] Hold it!
What's your problem?
I can't believe that...
that you would just go and
leave Hakkai behind like that!
None of us forced
him to stay behind.
That's not the point!
I've had enough!
Weren't you listening? Did you
not hear one word Hakkai said?
Gojyo, Goku, trust
me on this one, okay?
[Gojyo] Cheer up, Goku.
Hakkai did say that he...
didn't plan to die, yanno.
Leave him.
Hakkai...
[Demons growling and snarling]
[Hakkai] I don't normally
like to be this pushy, but...
[Gairu] Have you
lost your senses?
The four of you
couldn't handle us.
So what makes you think you
can do it any better alone?
You'll find out soon enough.
Of course...
By that time, it'll be
too late to beg for mercy.
Beg for mercy?
I think you may have things
backward, my friend.
Take one more step,
and you will die.
Well then...
Shall we get started?
Kill him!
[Demons yell and growl]
[Hakkai yells]
[Hakkai grunts in pain]
[Pained yelling]