[Goku] Sanzo!
Sanzo! Sanzo!
[Hakkai] Don't move him, Goku!
[Goku] SANZO!
[Shuei] Kouryuu...
I did this with my own hands.
[Shuei screams]
[Shuei] No please! Please don't!
Please don't erase me!
Serves you right!
That's what you get for
betraying your own kind
to take the side of demons you
weak pathetic preist!
[Rikudo laughs]
[Gojyo] What's wrong, Goku?
[Hakkai] You don't look so good.
[Gojyo] Goku!
[Hakkai] Will you get a hold
of yourself!?
[Hakkai] His power limiter!
[Gojyo] It broke off!
[Goku screams]
Goku!
Gojyo, get back!
Goku? Is that...
Yes it is. Without the limiter
he's reverted to his
original form.
A creature conceived in a giant
stone where the earthly
auras gathered.
A great sage; Goku!
At last your true form
is revealed!
Looks like you're the demons
after all!
Such speed.
Goku!
He's strong enough to
resist talismans?!
Sanzo told me Goku could get
pretty insane, but I had
no idea.
You can be impressed later!
We've still got a chance to
save Sanzo.
I think the spear missed his
vital organs.
We've got to get him out of
the rain.
Inside I may be able to stop
the bleeding.
[Gojyo] Missed his
vital organs?!
So there's still an unconscious
part in him that's still...
[Hakkai] I'll find someway to
take care of Sanzo.
Right now you've got to
stop Goku!
Thanks. Nice of you to give me
the easy job.
Well genius, if Sanzo were
concious I'd ask him.
But if we don't find a way to
reign in Goku quick there won't
be a building left standing
around here.
So you just better figure
something out. Now do it!
He got away!
[Rikudo] I'm not running! I will
return and when I do,
all of you demons better prepare
to feast on my talismans!
See? That's what happens when
you let your talisman do all
the thinking for you.
I'm sure he'll be back.
At least I was able to
lose Sanzo's wound.
For now all we have left to
worry about is...
[Gojyo] Goku...
Hey, you all right?
Get back, Gojyo! In this state
he'll strike out at anything
that moves!
Now he tells me!
Shit! He's not playing around.
Chew on this you freak!
Gojyo no!
It's just a figure of speach!
Now let go of my arm!
Ouch!
[Merciful Goddess] Hold
him still!
What?! Say what?!
Goku?
[Gojyo] He's asleep.
[Hakkai] What just happened?
[Merciful] You guys
are pathetic.
Boo!
Who- Who the hell are you?
Who the hell is that little
chimp? Son of a bitch!
They're the ones who made me
like this!
I'll kill them! I'll kill every
last one of them!
You're journey has hardly begun
and your little gang is already
in utter chaos.
Hey! Where do you get off, lady?
[Jiroushin] You, show
some respect!
You're speaking to the
embodiment of benevolence her
highness, the Merciful Goddess!
One of only Five Bodhisattvas
who rule the Heavens.
[Gojyo] She's the Merciful
Goddess?
You must be the one responcible
for placing on Goku's
power limiter.
[Merciful] Yes, that would be
me. And that little runt doesn't
require any regular coronet
either. I might add.
Only the gods have the ability
to forge a limiter
out of materials capable of
restraining Goku's powers.
Take my advice and keep a close
eye on this one.
Now him, he's still a problem,
I'm afraid.
He's taken quite a thrashing.
[Hakkai] He's lost quite a bit
of blood, there's nothing more
that I can do for him.
[Merciful] I got it.
Nothing is impossible for me!
♪Nothing's impossibe for me,♪
[Hakkai] Okay. Are Goddesses
always this sure of themselves?
[Merciful] ♪I'm a Goddess!♪
[Jiroushin] Oh boy, just trying
working for one.
[Merciful] ♪I can do whatever I
want to.♪
You! With the long purple hair,
and lots of spare blood, get
over here!
Come on, move your ass!
Look here, honey, I don't care
if you are a goddess!
I don't recall making any vows
that say that I have to-
Well, that will do.
Though I have tasted better.
What's the big idea you-?
[Hakkai] Gojyo!
I'd take it easy if I were
you, honey,
I just sucked out a few prime
pints of AB negative.
[Gojyo] Don't you need my
permission to do that?
You aren't going to like this,
Konzen Douji.
Or should I call you Genjo
Sanzo now?
Whoever you are, if you want to
live through the night,
you're just going to have to
deal with it.
Sanzo, you're awake!
[Mericful] Yes. I can see that.
It was probably just an
unconscious reaction.
My, such strong reflexes though.
I can see he's already getting
his strength back.
[Hakkai] Thank you so much.
[Merciful] If you want to thank
me, give me your body in return.
That's all the payment I need.
This wasn't about charity.
The fact is you're on a very
important mission right now.
And honestly it wouldn't be any
fun if you died today.
Ta-ta for now.
[Merciful] Such an unruly band
of misfits.
You know, they just might make
it after all.
[Door opens]
[Hakkai] Goku, you still here?
Waiting by the bed won't make
him wake any sooner, won't you
at least eat something?
No, I'm fine.
You really don't remember what
happened to you when your
limiter fell off, do you?
[Goku] I remember the blood
gushing from Sanzo's stomach,
then the world turning white,
all sorts of ideas started
spinning through my head.
Come to think of it, I wonder
who that was?
He looked like Sanzo,
yet different.
I can't remember why I was
imprisoned for so long.
I had to have done something
truely terrible though.
I mean why else would they lock
me away in Mount Gogyou?
With nothing to do but watch the
sky for years and years in some
craggy prison cell.
Until a golden light finally
reached down and saved me.
He was the ray of sun I had been
longing for.
[Goku] Sanzo's always been my
savior, even though I can do
anything to save him.
Well, I think the one thing you
can do for him,
is to be sure to never let
him down.
Don't you remember what Sanzo
told us? He said that we would
never die.
We should take care not to do
anything reckless, so that we
can see this mission through
to the end.
You're right. Yeah.
Be strong!
I won't fail you, Sanzo.
I promise.
Sanzo's unconcious, Gojyo's
still anemic, and you're in
a funk,
so I guess the only thing left
for me to do is cook.
Hey what a fantastic idea!
I'll get the kitchen ready.
Whadda know. Sanzo, you're the
only person who could've gotten
Goku that depressed.
Do me a favor, and don't reopen
the wound we worked so hard
to close.
I'd really hate for you and
I to be left with the same scar.
This is ccrazy.
Damnit...
[Knock at the door]
[Gojyo] Hey, droopy-eyes...
I don't suppose you're planning
on going after Rikudo, are ya?
Well if you are then feel free
to just go through the window
in there.
They told me to keep an eye on
you, but who am I to get in
your way, right?
Man, I can't get away with
anything when you guys are
around, huh?
With an attitude like that,
maybe I should come in there
and stop you.
Ah relax, I'm just
kiddin' around.
So those prayer beads around
Rikudo's neck, would those
be yours?
So what if they are?
I thought so.
They lit up, as if they were
some forcefield trying to
protect him.
That necklace is probably
what's keeping the last
piece of Shuei alive.
Once the talisman becomes
powerful enough there won't
be any Shuei left to save.
Well, not that I care what
happens to you,
but the other two tend to get
a little sentimental about
things, you know.
You're a popular guy, Sanzo.
[sarcasticly] Yep, everybody
loves me.
[Gojyo] See you around, pal.
[Rikudo] The prayer beads are
sensing something in the forest,
as if I'm being drawn there.
By someone!
Some one I know!
[Rikudo] Kouryuu!
I'll be... You managed
to survive.
Did you crawl back so I could
finish the job, is that it?
No, I came to kill you with my
own two hands.
I thought as much.
[Kouryuu] Shuei, I have
something for you.
[Shuei] But these are the beads
they found on you in the river.
Are you sure?
Try and kill me if you
can, Kouryuu!
[Rikudo] Now you will know
some of the suffering I have
had to endure!
Because you fled the temple like
a coward!
Repent!
My mistake for thinking you were
able to take care of yourself.
What makes you think you'll do
any better defending yourself
against me?
I'm not a demon.
I just figured it out.
I know what the talisman
hungers for.
Your soul, Kouryuu! Your soul!
[Rikudo] Your aim is off too.
That wound I gave you
must be aching.
[Sanzo] When you struck it
wasn't Goku I was trying
to protect.
It was another wound that has
yet to heal.
I'd really hate for you and I to
be left with the same scars.
But the other two tend to get
a little sentimental about
things, you know.
Yeah. Be strong.
Willing to die for no one,
living for no one
except myself.
Vowing to never again care for
someone so much I couldn't
bear to lose them.
This is my mantra.
Great spirits, bring winter's
chill to my enemy's bones,
make his body turn from flesh
to stone,
he who would do harm to me, hold
him fast! Make him freeze!
That chant...
It's a spell that works on
humans and spirits!
I'm paralized.
My, my, this is just
too precious.
I get to kill you as easily as
tearing the wings off a bird!
[Rikudo] Feel your life slipping
away? This is what it's been
like for me since you left!
I've waited so long for you to
share my nightmare!
No thanks, Shuei.
Maybe I left Kinzan Temple,
but as for the talisman
you carry,
you let it control you because
you're weak!
You're weak!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I wish your sorry soul had
never existed!
Shuei...
Araya's Spell is too strong.
In a few moments the talisman
will have consumed the last
bit of him.
Nothing can stop that now.
Nothing.
[Rikudo] K-Kouryuu...
[Shuei] Someone said you were an
evil spirit,
but just now, sitting in the
window, you looked like
something else.
[Kouryuu] Did I? What was that?
If only you had never
existed Kouryuu,
Then I could have let
go sooner!
Shuei...
[Kouryuu] I have no place
for gods.
Though I cannot believe in
deities, I do believe in myself.
[Shuei] How very like you.
[Kouryuu] I've never given
anyone anything before now,
so yes, I'm sure.
Guard them well.
[Gunshot]
[Shuei] Thank you.
Oh, look, Kouryuu, it seems
that the birds are returning
to the North.
I wonder, who do you think it
was that decided that the birds
are actually free?
Even if they can fly where
they please,
however, if they find there is
no end to their journey
or no safe place to rest their
weary wings,
they may regret having those
wings at all.
Perhaps true freedom...
Perhaps true freedom is having a
home to return to.
Anybody looking for a ride?
It'll only cost you 10,000 yen.
[Sanzo] You wouldn't happen to
be heading West?
I'm crashing. Anyone who wakes
me up I'll cut their nuts off.
[Hakkai chuckles]
[Hakkai] Go to sleep.
And so, our little band of
misfits continues their
journey to the West.
Theses guys would rather bite
their own tongues off,
than be forced to dance to
someone else's tune.
Some people don't change in five
hundred years.
No matter how many times
they die...
they're reborn...
[Goku] He's got a vague way of
saying things.
And the looks of a snake that's
about to strike.
And he really pisses me off!
He better no mess with me.
Who is this "fortune-teller"
named Chin Yisou?
Who knows. But I hope
he's dangerous.
Next time on Saiyuki:
"The Death Sear"
Let's rumble!