[Goku] Gojyo, you son of a
bitch! You cheated!
[Gojyo] The more stupid they
are, the more they try to
blame it on somebody else.
Oh yeah? Well answer me this,
fat had! How do you get four
aces three times in a row?!
How?!
How?! By cheating, that's how!
[Gojyo] Look, don't blame me
because you're stupid.
[Goku] I'm stupid for playing
cards with you.
[Sanzo] God, I wish you and I
could just do this alone!
[Gojyo] No you're just stupid!
[Goku] That's it, I'm kicking
your ass!
[Gojyo] Well, if you think you
can do that
[Hakkai] Uh-huh, but then it
wouldn't be nearly as much fun.
[Gojyo] then you're more stupid
than I thought you were!
Holy shit that's cold!
Look dragon, next time watch
where you're going, will ya?!
[Gojyo] Help! I'm gonna drown!
[Goku] Wow, take a look at you.
[Gojyo] Come on, don't just
stand there!
[Gojyo] Help me, asshole!
[Goku] I've never seen you move
with this much energy ever.
Oh I move just like this all the
time, in the bed.
In bed, eh?
You mean like a water bed!
[Gojyo and Goku clamoring to be
let out from under the water]
[Shunrei laughs]
Oh gosh, I'm so sorry.
It's just that it's been a long
time since I've seen grown men
acting like little boys.
You jerks damage my
reputation daily.
[Shunrei] You're soaking wet.
You can come dry off at
my place.
I've got food, hot tea, and more
importantly for you, I've
got towels.
Wow, they fit just perfectly.
Yes, thank you.
Yeah, thanks a lot. Hope you let
me keep 'em.
You can't keep them. You will
happily return them when your
clothes are dry.
No, really, it's actually
nice to see someone wearing
them again.
[Han] Oh all right, enough talk.
Oh thank you. It looks great.
Please sit down and eat before
everything gets cold.
No way! Auntie, you know how
to cook!
[Han] Why thank you!
No, thank you!
[Gojyo] Put it on a plate
first, pig!
[Goku] Mind your own business!
[Hakkai] Thank you so much for
you hospitality.
[Sanzo] Goku, don't make a mess.
[Gojyo] Hey shit head, what
about the rest of us?
[Sanzo] They're not my friends,
I just want to go on record.
[Han] I'm so glad all of you
are here.
It's nice to see Shunrei
smile again.
She's been alone for so
long now.
[Goku] Really?
She was in love once, a long
time ago.
Really?
[Han] He was a demon.
About a year ago, a change came
over him, just like it did all
the others.
But he left, before he became
like the others, angry, hungry.
Shunrei still looks off hoping
he will come back some day.
She goes down to river to wash
once a week, like a ritual,
cleaning clothes that haven't
been worn in months.
I think she wakes everday
thinking this is the day
he will return.
Damn and she looks hot too.
Don't even think about it.
Then these clothes, they
belonged to him then,
didn't they?
Well, they certainly aren't
mine, are they?
I wish I had someone who would
do this for me every week.
Wow, it smells so clean!
These things must mean a great
deal to her.
I'm a little surprised she would
let us wear them.
I'm sure it's just a way to
thank you,
perhaps for giving her something
to smile about for once.
Oh my heavens, it may just be
the fact that each of you boys
are every bit as handsome
as her boyfriend was.
Jien was a very good looking
man, you know.
Jien?!
What's up? You know him?
It's a common name.
Probably not.
A common name? He's full of
shit? What's going on?
What's he hiding?
[Goku] Don't patronize me!
I don't have any secrets!
Well not big ones anyway.
Okay let's change the subject.
[Gojyo] Hey...
Oh hello.
I don't suppose you got a
picture of this boyfriend
of yours?
I can see my aunt has been
talking again.
Why do you want to see a
picture of him?
Just curious to see the guy who
would cause a nice girl like you
so much saddness, that's all.
No, I don't have any pictures.
He was a demon, wasn't
he, Shunrei?
Yes. Do you think there's
something wrong with that?
He was one of the most wonderful
men I've ever met.
Not a day goes by that I don't
think of him.
I believe in him.
And I believe he'll come back
to me.
That's why I clean this empty
room and wash clothes that no
one wears.
It's foolish, but it gives
me hope. Do you understand?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to hurt
your feelings.
No you didn't. Honestly.
Listen to me.
Your boyfriend and I have a lot
in common.
Okay I give. I can't take it
anymore. Who is this Jien guy?
Relax will you? It's not like
Gojyo's keeping it a secret.
But even though it's not a big
secret exactly, I wouldn't bring
it up if I were you, my friend.
Jien is Gojyo's half-brother.
[Gojyo] What I'm try to say is,
I'm a demon too.
Half-breed, actually.
What's the matter, Shunrei?
Don't you believe me?
[Shein] Don't you believe me?
It's not that. I do.
And I want to thank you for
telling me.
It's just... I haven't talked
about him in a long time.
That's all.
Come on, don't cry.
You know, it's not fair to turn
on the tears like that.
What do you mean?
It makes me want to kiss you.
[Shunrei] You're weird.
[Goku] Okay now I got it!
Gojyo's mother is human and
Jien's mother is a demon, right?
Yes, Jien is Gojyo's older
brother, and a full-blooded
demon, because his father
was also a demon.
You're not all that good at
geneology, are you?
Gojyo didn't have it easy, not
as a kid.
All because he was born of mixed
heritage of a father who was a
demon and a human mother.
[Goku] Why?
Because most people believe a
child born
from both demon and man will
bring nothing but misfortune
and pain.
That sucks!
[Gojyo] It does.
But you know what Hakkai didn't
tell you? That it's true.
Yep, I'm gonna bring you pain.
[Goku] Aw knock it off,
you freak!
My god, are those guys going to
sleep all day?
Well, Shunrei, good morning!
[Shunrei] Oh hello! And good
morning to you too.
Oh if you're looking for my
aunt, she's around back.
Thakn you.
Good morning, Han.
Good morning! So what do you
have for me today?
That's just it, I don't have
much for you today.
Demons attacked yesterday in the
woods to the west. I've been
afraid to go out.
Oh no, that's just terrible.
These bastards were smart,
attacked in a pack.
I heard they were lead by one
with silver-hair, mean son of
a bitch. Killed most of them.
[Han] Oh no.
Shunrei! Shunrei!
Wake up!
Oh good morning, to you too.
Time for breakfast?
[Han] No! It's Shunrei,
she's gone!
Where would she go?
She went to the forest, to the
woods to the west of here!
One of the farmers told me about
a pack of demons that attacked
in the woods.
Shunrei heard him say they
were lead by a demon with
silver hair.
And she think it's Jien.
You've got to go after her and
bring her back.
Jien...
Jien!
Yes. We'll go get her and bring
her back, don't you worry.
Hopefully bring her back alive.
Jien, Jien, where are you?
I can't believe she ran out
alone! What the hell was
she thinking?!
You'd run a lot faster if your
mouth was closed.
She couldn't have gotten that
much of a head start on us.
She's gotta be close by!
She better be, because I don't
know about you guys,
but the last time I checked,
none of us happened to have
a bloodhound handy.
Gojyo's right. We'll never find
her in these woods.
You should have brought that
stupid dragon. Your bad.
[Hakkai] You're not helping.
We split up.
Gojyo and Hakkai, go west.
Goku and I will take the
east side.
[Goku] Got it.
[Gojyo] Let's go.
Jien! Jein...
I heard they were lead by one
with silver hair. Mean son of
a bitch. Killed most of them.
Oh God please, don't let it be
you, Jien. Please.
[Shunrei] Jien?
Well? Anything?
Well I take it as a compliment
you think my nose is so good,
but no I can't smell a thing.
We've got to find her and fast.
I hope Gojyo and Hakkai are
having better luck than we
are. For Shunrei's sake.
[Hakkai] Shunrei! Shunrei!?
Shunrei why did you do this?
You'd think I'd be use to
women crying.
I grew up with it.
Mother...
...she was a river of tears.
And I... I was its source.
Maybe it wasn't just me. Maybe
she just saw the shadow of the
man she loved in me.
and the ghost of the woman who
bore me.
What kind of woman would try to
kill her own son?
Would the pain have ceased?
Would my death have stopped all
those tears?
Would they have stopped
my brothers?
Gojyo, are you alright?
Get your hands off me!
What's the matter with you?
You're not made that I told
everybody about your brother,
are you?
If it was suppose to be a secret
I'm sorry.
No dude, it's cool
[Hakkai] It's just that Goku was
just all bent out of shape
about it.
Sometimes it's hard in this
group, you feel kind of left
out. I'm sorry, really.
[Gojyo] Tch, he really is just a
noisy little bastard, isn't
he? Jerk.
Well I wouldn't go that far, but
you're entitled to your opinion.
Aw, come on you know, he's such
a brat.
Actually, I was talking
about me.
I'm sorry, I thought I
was clear.
Damn, these guys are making me
look like the san one.
[Shunrei screams]
Damnit, I hate it when they
make noise.
I don't know man, I kind of
like it.
Take it easy guys, you're gonna
scare her.
HELP!
[Both] No!
Well done! We couldn't have
done better if we had done
it ourselves,
and believe me we wanted to.
Shunrei, are you all right?
I am, I'm fine.
Okay she's fine, I say these
weasles still pay for what they
tried to do to her!
Oh is that right? Well then
tell me,
who are you that you think you
can make ME pay?
So you don't know. You don't
know who we are or why we
came here?
Somehow I don't think they
weren't sent by Kougaiji.
Who cares who sent them.
They still need to be
taught some manners.
Amen!
[Demon 1] Alright, that's it!
[Demon 2] That's it!
You guys are nothing but food
to us!
It's very flattering, guys, but
we're not interested.
Hey, why are we still talking to
these assholes?
No wait! Haven't you seen him?
I'm looking for someone, his
name is Jien. He has silver
hair, just like you!
Jien? Silver hair?
What do I look like? A freakin'
information service?
I don't know!
I've never seen anyone with my
hair color anywhere, like it's
any of your business!
It wasn't Jien. He's not here.
[Goku] Shunrei! Are you okay?!
[Hakkai] She's okay, Goku. It's
just been too much for her.
She'll be alright. We just need
to take her home.
Yep. Sounds like a plan to me. I
say we get the hell out of here.
[Hakkai] Her aunt must be
worried. We need to get back.
[Goku] Yeah I bet.
[Silver] Hey! You think you can
just walk away like that?!
We're not so easy to ignore,
you know!
Especially you, headband, you
should stay.
Maybe you'd like to hear about a
half breed me and my friends
have heard about.
It's a guy with red hair and
eyes who looks a lot like you.
[Silver] You listening to me?!
I wonder if you're a true
red head! Down below I mean.
Ha! Why don't you come show us?
Oh man, I wouldn't go there if I
were you.
They should mind their
own business.
Let's teach these guys
some manners.
Aw don't worry about it, Goku.
I'm flattered.
[Shunrei] Thanks for being
honest with me.
You know, I hope the day will
come soon when humans
and demons,
well I'd like things to be...
someday as they were, if
not better.
And if I had a child, he'd be
happy, accepted.
That's it! I'm tired of your
attitude, red head!
Now we're gonna waste you like
we did those humans yesterday!
You spilled blood?
Yes and we'll spill more!
So yeah, wanna see if the carpet
matches the drapes, do yeah?
Sorry guys,
only the best looking girls get
to find that out.
[Shunrei] Han?
Yes, Shunrei, I'm right here.
What happened to me? All I
remember was going to the
woods to look for Jien,
then they came to help me and...
Oh my god, Auntie are they
alright? Please tell me!
Oh they're fine, dear, and they
went about on their way.
I tried to get them to stay
until you woke, but they
couldn't.
Oh no...
I- I didn't even get a chance to
thank them.
They know dear, I think they do
know how you feel about them.
They said they were on a journey
to set things right.
To return things to the way they
once were.
When we all lived together
as one.
The red haired one, he told me
to tell you that Jien would come
back to you someday.
[Shunrei] Oh god look at me.
[Han] What's wrong, Shunrei?
[Shunrei] Nothing.
It's just that...
I'm glad Gojyo can't see
me crying.
[Goku] Okay, so the guy Shunrei
likes isn't your brother? Did I
get that right?
That's right, my brother doesn't
have silver hair.
There's another missed
opportunity.
Come again?
She's not my sister-in-law, we
could've had some fun.
Gah, you never fail to
dissapoint me, you know that?
And you know what, Hakkai?
I hope I never do.
[Sanzo] We've got a job to do.
Tell Hakuryu to step on it.
Why are you looking at me like
that? It's not too much to ask.
Right? You know what I want.
The world?
What an insignificant part of
the plan.
Oh, I couldn't care less.
What is the world compaired to
you, my beloved, Gyumaoh?
To have you return to us again,
that is my desire!
And the world will be mine once
your resurection is complete!
You can allow no one to get in
my way! No one, not even those
that call themselves gods!
I believe I've made
myself clear.
Yes, I guarentee it.
Good. Spoken like a true son and
heir of Gyumaoh.
Son to him, as you are now son
to me.
And if your real mother
was released from her
pillaresque prison,
I'm sure her voice would
accompany mine in both wish and
devotion, my young protege.
Yes, Mother.
I will do exactly as
you command.
As long as my true mother is
imprisoned, I'm yours.
This I vow.
Yet I promise you, true mother,
that I will fight any demon,
any man, to free you!
[Goku] Well, it seems this
Kougaiji wimp is too chickenshit
to come after us himself.
So instead, he sends this girl
to fight us. How lame is that?
I mean, she's kinda cute and
all, but does she really think
she can take down the four
of us?
Well, she could probably take
down Gojyo cause he's lame.
[Gojyo] I'm so gonna kick
your ass.
[Goku] Haha, yeah.
Anyway, check out this next
episdoe: "A Beautiful Assassin"