[Goku] We aren't really going to
camp out here, are we?
At least we'll be able to get
out of the rain for a few hours.
[Hakkai] Come on, pull it tight.
[Goku] Damn.
The rain always puts Sanzo
in a bad mood.
I think Hakkai told me why
once, but I've forgotten.
Well, that's got nothing to do
with me anyway.
I don't hate rain that much.
It was my past that always
poured down on me in droves.
I never minded getting
little muddy.
Then again, maybe I convinced
myself the rain could wash
the memories away.
I had been unwilling
to forget.
I use to think like that.
But I'm not the only one here
with scars to heal.
You couldn't severe the bond
between us, even if you tried.
Now that I think about it,
that night three years ago,
it rained like this too.
"The Storm of Fate"
[Gojyo] Aces, four of a kind.
[Girl 1] Yeah!
[Girl 2] You're amazing!
Hey, come on, Gojyo, give me a
break already, will ya?
It's too early to start
complaining, Tongpu.
You still have a few bucks I
haven't won yet.
[Girl 1] That's right.
[Girl 2] The night's
still young.
Tell you what, if I win this
hand here, the next round is
on me, girls.
[All Three] You can do
it, Gojyo!
Wait a minute, is every woman
in this place rooting for
you, Gojyo?
[Girl 4] Of course we are.
You do have the most fantastic
mane of hair.
You must tell me who dyes it?
And you have the most
beautiful eyes too.
[Gojyo] On second thought, let's
call it a night.
[Girl 1] What?
[Gojyo] Bartender, put the
drinks on my tab.
[Girl 2] Gojyo, no wait!
See you later.
[Girl 3] You idiot, he's super
sensitive about his hair.
You can't so much as mention
it around him.
[Girl 4] What?! Why?!
[Girl 3] No one knows.
I get through my days living
off my winnings in cards,
and survive the nights by
seducing women with
cheap words.
In a way, living is
disgustingly easy.
That is, so long as I never
have to look anyone in
the eyes.
Pretty hair she says, I don't
know about that.
To me, it looks rather...
What's up with this guy?
[Gojyo] Hello? You dead?
Huh, hey, you're alive!
He looked at me.
And it almost looked as if
he laughed at me too.
Are you saying it was
a mass murder?
[Sanbutsushin A] Yes, two months
ago, the Dark Crow Clan.
Then just a short time ago,
the Hyakugan Maoh's Clan
met the same fate.
A thousand we lost.
[Sanzo] A thousand, you say?
[Sabbutsushin B] Genjo Sanzo...
[Sanzo] Yes.
We call on you to track down
the atrocious criminal who
has done this.
Cho Gonou, a youth who is no
longer human.
Cho Gonou...
If this is Hell, it all looks
rather commonplace.
Well, excuse me for keeping the
place so plain.
You sure took your sweet time
waking up.
Sheesh, the doctor said you
needed to rest and wouldn't
let me smoke around you.
But I'm smoking now! Believe me!
You got that?
Oh, of course, you go ahead.
Aw, forget it.
Tell me, were you the one
ho saved me?
[Gojyo] You know, it too bad.
[Cho] What?
You might have been much better
off if you were in Hell.
[Gojyo] Do you wish you
were dead?
[Tea kettle whistles]
[Cho] No, to be honest, I think
it's better that it turned out
this way.
I'm grateful that you saved me.
You were comatose for about a
week. I stuffed most of your
innards in back myself.
But you should be okay. I hope.
[Gojoy] I wouldn't try any sit
ups for a while if I were you.
Alright.
I'm out of beans I'm afraid,
you'll have to make do
with instant.
[Cho] Thank you.
[Gojyo] I also had a doctor
friend of mine take a look
at you.
He said you'll be up to speed
in about a month or two.
So, just make sure and rest
for now.
Oh yeah, for your information,
this is the one and only time
I take a man to bed, you got it?
I do.
[Monk A] Master Sanzo
is here!
[Monk B] Thank the gods.
[Sanzo] What's all the
commotion about?
It's just... that boy.
[Goku] Oh, Sanzo!
Welcome back!
He let some filthy stray dog
into the compound.
They've been knocking over altar
articles, it's completely out
of control.
[Goku] Look, Sanzo.
[Sanzo] Why you...
...dumb monkey.
[Goku] That hurt!
What'd you do that for, Sanzo?!
[Sanzo] You know damn well what
I did that for.
That boy is becoming such
a burden.
[Monk A] Why Master would ever
take in such a troublesome child
I will never
[Goku] It looked so hungry!
[Monk A] understand. I just
doesn't make any sense to me.
[Sanzo] Get washed and
changed, now!
[Monk B] I totall agree.
[Goku] I'm going, I'm going!
[Monk A] I'm sorry, Master,
Please forgive us!
Sometimes I wonder why I ever
bothered with him.
It was so damn noisy for
one thing.
His voice kept calling out, it
really grated on my nerves.
When I had enough I went over
to smack him one.
But then he looked up at me
with that stupid look on
his face,
I lost my will to strike.
What's with the piece, you
going somewhere?
Afraid so. Unfortunatly, I've
been given the task of tracking
down a certain someone.
[Goku] Let me go with you!
[Sanzo] I refuse. Why should I
take some troublesome animal
with me?
[Goku] Who're you calling
an animal?!
That'd be you. Don't you know
who you are?
Aw come on, I don't wanna be
left behind here with the monks!
[Monk A] Why Master would ever
take in such a troublesome child
I will never understand.
[Goku] Please, Sanzo!
[Sanzo] You really are a pain
in the ass.
Hurry up, you little monkey.
Let's get moving.
[Goku] Wait up, Sanzo!
[Cho] Full house...
[Gojyo] Not bad at all.
And here I was going easy on
you because you're an invalid.
As far as you know.
Oh, sorry about that.
[Cho] You never ask anything
about me.
You know, I'm not all that
interested, frankly.
[Cho] Since I've already
troubled you so much,
would you mind terribly if
I stayed until I'm able
to get around?
Got anywhere to go?
No, but I do have one piece of
unfinished business.
How about that? Now I have the
full house this time!
Oh, I'm sorry, but I happen to
have a straight flush.
Okay, what's the deal? I do
his for a living, you know.
Are you a professional?
For some reason these things
just come easily to me.
But even if I can read the flow
of the game,
I still need a lot of luck on my
side to win.
Guess I'm not making much sense.
[Gojyo] You're one of those
clever poor guy types,
aren't you?
[Cho] I guess I am.
I am too.
Sanzo, I'm thinking if this
Cho Gonou guy killed a
thousand demons,
and became a demon himself, he's
a real bad dude, right?
[Sanzo] Who can say?
Something about this mission
just doesn't seem right.
I know nothing about this man
beyond a physical description.
Why did the Sanbutsushin send
me to pursue an ordinary
demon murderer?
[Woman A] Something's wrong with
Gojyo.
[Woman B] You're telling me,
he didn't try to hit on me
once yesterday.
[Man A] Didn't he say something
about taking in some wounded
guy about a month ago?
Someone with green eyes and
pretty face, that's when
it started.
Sanzo?
I'd like to more about this
wounded man your friend has
taken in.
Why look for a wounded man at my
friends house,
when there's a perfectly
healthy, totally hot number
right here?
I'll be you all carry big guns
in your robes.
The sterotype happens
to be true.
Do you happen to have a moment?
Sure, are you leaving?
I am.
But there is something I want
to tell you before I go.
I've killed so many with the
blade of my ego, and I murdered
everyone of them in the name
of revenge.
I have one thing left to do then
I intend to accept whatever
punishment I have coming.
I am truly grateful to you for
saving my life that night.
Perhaps this is my act
of penitence.
Penitence?
The color of your hair and eyes
remind me of...
...the color of the blood that
I have spilled.
[Cho] The crimson that stains my
hands is what keeps me grounded
in reality,
even as I attampt to escape the
weight of my sins.
Your hair and your eyes are
the only things that admonish
me, Gojyo.
I see.
[Cho] Well, I'll be going now.
[Gojoy] Sure...
[Gojyo] Maybe what I wanted was
someone who could only
see blood
in this crimson color,
just like I do.
[Gojyo] Say...
I still don't know your name.
My name is-
[knock at the door]
Hold on a sec.
[Gojyo] Yeah, yeah, who is it?
[Sanzo] Sorry to disturb you
so late,
but I'm on a hunt for a
diabolical criminal,
who has commited mass murder.
[Sanzo] A young man in his
twenties with green eyes.
He goes by the name
of Cho Gonou.
Really? Don't know him.
Don't play dumb. I know for a
fact that you took this mad
man into your own home.
[Gojyo] And I'm telling you I've
never heard of him.
Who the hell are you anyway?
What kind of a monk goes around
hunting murderers?
Let me go.
[Gojyo] What if I say no?
[Gojyo] Bastard!
You'll pay for that.
You're a dead man.
What denomination did you say
you were, Buddah?
The kind that doesn't forbid my
kicking your ass.
Just because you belong to an
order, doesn't mean I have to
follow yours.
You want to die that
badly, do ya?
I don't die easily.
[Gunshot]
You damn Buddah thumper.
Now I don't want to have
to bloody up those luscious
locks of yours, pretty boy.
Stop it, Gojyo!
You stay inside now!
So you're Cho Gonou?
[Sanzo] You bastard...
I always did do better when
I'm on top.
[Gojyo] Hurry up and run!
I said go!
Goku!
[Gojyo] So you brought a
friend with you?
I just have to beat this guy,
am I right?
Damn...
He actually managed to block
Goku's attack!
Sanzo, this guy might actually
be pretty good!
[Sanzo] Don't act so happy!
Then I'll take it seriously now!
What is that brat on?
He's fast!
No fair.
[Sanzo] Goku!
Please don't move,
and just listen to me.
[Cho] Don't blame him for any
of this. He has nothing to
do with me.
It's true that I have committed
henious sins.
But there is just one thing
I have left to do.
Time...
I just need to have a little
more time.
I apologize for everything.
[Goku] Hey!
[Cho] In all honesty, I've
desired to be condemned
to Hell,
ever since I lost what was
precious to me.
Which is?
To me, she was my true love,
but in someways was also
like my older sister.
She gently embraced everything.
I did love the way she was so
open to the world.
I made a promise that I would
always protect her,
that I would always be with her
no matter what happened.
But... You know how people
often talk about premonitions?
Well, when all those terrible
things were happening to her,
I was completely oblivious.
It was just another day working
with my students.
I couldn't sense it.
Why couldn't I know
what was happening,
and run to protect her when she
needed me the most?
[Gojyo] That's the way life
is, isn't it?
It doesn't mean you didn't love
her, so don't blame yourself.
No that I'm in a position
to say.
I don't have anything that's
precious to me, so I
wouldn't know.
What the heck is love anyway?
Not that I want it.
[Gojyo] I let my hair grow out
as a lesson to myself,
and to hide the scars from when
my mother almost killed me.
The color of blood that's
like admonishment...
I thought I was the only one
who saw it that way.
So it appears that love was the
source of both our pain.
The love that I couldn't
win, the love that he
couldn't protect.
That night as we both
blamed ourselves for
being so powerless,
the phantoms of our memories
vanished in a sea of blood.
So he's called Cho Gonou?
That name really doesn't
fit him.
And you're telling me he never
told you anything?
[Gojyo] That's what I've been
saying all along.
I don't know why you haven't
been listening to me.
And another thing, I don't
see why I'm responcible
for feeding your pet.
You're pushing your luck.
Hey, this is really good!
Can I finish it? Can I?
You trying to eat me out
of house and home, you
stupid monkey?!
I'm not a monkey! My name's
Goku, you deginerate!
Well I think stupid monkey is
the most accurate.
Well, he did go without eating
for about five hundred years.
So his body must be trying to
make up for it.
[Gojyo] What's up with that?
You certainly are eccentric.
Why did you take him in if you
knew it would cause problems
for you?
[Gojyo] Good question. I'm not
sure I know the answer.
[Goku] Hey, Sanzo, is he really
a bad guy?
Why do you ask?
For some reason he just didn't
seem like a bad guy to me.
Murder doesn't necessarily
mean evil, right?
The world being what it is a lot
of people out there deserve to
die, don't they?
But those who do take it apon
themselves to kill others have
to be prepared to have others
try to kill them as well.
And that's what they call the
law of karma, my friends.
That's why, good or bad, the
ones who are going to be
left standing
are those with the strongest
wills to survive.
Will to live, huh? Too bad
you're a monk.
And what is that supposed
to mean?
So where does that leave us?
What are we going to do now?
Do we just let him go?
Listen, I may not like it,
but this is still my
assigned mission.
Even if it is a pain in the ass.
[Gojyo] I'm afraid you're
wasting your time.
I don't know what kind of
unfinished business he has,
but whatever it is,
he's gonna do it.
And then he'll probably die.
That's just the kind of guy
he is.
[Sanzo] If that's true, that's
even more reason for me to
find him.
My instructions are to capture
Cho Gonou and bring him to the
Palace of the Setting Sun alive.
I can't have him dying at his
own convenience!
Sorry to bother you.
Hey...
Count me in.
[Sanzo] As the rain continues,
it washes away everything.
The sorrows, the pain,
the regrets.
Yes, even the sins.
As the crimson of blood turns
into the crimson of sunrise.
There is a new dawn of hope,
a ray of light that only
the living can see.
"An Ode to the Living"
Next on Saiyuki.