[Narrator] And so, to prevent
the resurrection of the grand
demon Gyumaoh,
the most high Merciful Goddess
sent Sanzo, Goku, Hakkai, and
Gojyo to India, far to the west.
Goddamnit, this one's hot.
Goku, get me another beer.
Get your own beer, jerkoff!
Okay. You're going to get me
another beer
or I'm going to take this can
and shove it up your whiny
little ass! You got that?
You just try and see what
happens you shit head!
Oh yeah?!
You're just looking for an
excuse to touch my ass,
aren't ya?
[Sanzo] [exsaperated] Please.
[Gojyo] You little fag!
Don't project your fantasies
on me!
Alright, that's it! Pull over,
I'm taking him out!
Your little unrequited love
affair is starting to get on
my nerves!
Get a room!
[Hakkai] Good move there,
uh Sanzo.
I thought so, thanks.
Oh my, awful quiet back there
guys. Are you making out?
[Gojyo] Shut up, Hakkai.
[Goku] Yeah, shut up.
[Merciful Goddess] West
and East.
Each has begun to stir.
To where the sun rises.
And beyond where it sun sets.
[Door opens]
[Jiroushin] I have a report from
the Sanbutsushin.
It has finally happened.
The motions for which began
long ago.
[Jiroushin] Pardon?
Five hundred years ago...
Since that moment!
[Goku] God! This food
is awesome!
[Goku] Hey, you H2O asshole, get
your hands off! That's mine!
[Goku] Give it back!
[Gojyo] Come on...
[Goku] Come on, jerkoff!
Give it!
[Gojyo] Yep, that's it.
[The two continue fighting over
the food.]
God! Give him his damn chicken
and order your own!
That poor little guy.
[Hakkai] Ah don't feel sorry
for him.
By the way, are you the magician
in the kitchen?
Yes. Do you like it?
[Goku] Wow, you're amazing!
I've never eaten this good in my
life, ever!
I'm mean it, thanks!
You're welcome. I'm glad you
like it.
Yeah, yeah right the food's
4 stars.
How's the demonic clientel
acting lately?
What's to say? They're scum.
Always were. One day they
started acting like their
true nature.
Ugly. Killed ten people in our
town then they just dissapeared.
So they congregate, attack,
then the group leaves.
Someone calls them, but to what
gathering place?
It's like a summoning that
grows louder. And they
follow it.
[Houmei] I wish every demons
would just disappear!
What they've done...
The things they've done!
They're monsters, all of
them monsters!
[Man] Houmei!
I'm sorry, one of those killed
was a dear friend of hers.
Will that be all?
[Hakkai] Too many crimes. The
humans die the survivors grieve.
They grow angry. Who could
blame them?
[Sanzo] They don't know the real
reason for what's happening,
it justifies their prejudice.
They're just humans. They're
stupid and judjmental what's
the mystery?
Their prejudice might not
threaten you,
but Goku and I have to wear
these little restraints,
and not everyone in town may
look at it as just fashion.
Huh. Speaking of him, where is
monkey boy?
[Sanzo] Eating out doggy bags.
You can bet on it.
[Houmei] Thanks for the help.
You're sweet.
[Goku] No problem. Sanzo's
fat butt means I get a lot
of practice.
[Houmei] I've had to do
everything by myself
since Ekitoku-
Ekitoku?
We've known each other since we
were kids.
He was killed by a demon.
Humans and demons should never
have been living together in the
first place!
It's not natural! Just look at
everything that's happened!
You agree with me, don't
you, Goku?!
You know... uh... I- I don't
think... I mean...
They're evil! Disgusting!
We should find a way to kill
every last one of them!
Don't you think so?
Um... Yeah.
[Hakkai] Goku, you didn't tell
her anything, did you?
I don't know if she'd handle it
all that well.
I hear that.
[Goku] Aw great the carnival's
in town.
[Gojyo] Oooh yeah.
I'd like to show a couple of
those little carnival hotties
what kind of action's going on
under my big top.
[Hakkai blows a whistle]
Too much information!
[Goku] The hotel's booked,
preacher man.
But I had the foresight to book
a couple of vacant singles. So
you can say thank you now.
"Thank you now"
I say we all stick together
tonight just in case the local
demon contingency
gets antsy and decides to go
for a midnight snack.
And if we do have to stick
together tonight,
I'm afraid I'll need a little
"me time" before bed. Later.
I can't wait.
It warms my heart to see all of
us getting along with eachother
so well.
Good times.
[Yaone] I have news, Lord
Kougaiji, movement in the East.
[Kougaiji] I know. Don't worry
about it.
I've already sent someone to
take care of the little matter.
Dispatched assasins,
I'm impressed.
[Kougaiji] I'm doing this for
you, Mother.
Don't worry, I'll release you
from this spell.
I promise!
[Goku snoring obnoxiously]
[Man] Houmei, let me get the
rest. You go on to bed.
Oh, I'm almost done.
[Man] Augh!
[Door opens]
Bastard, I'll kill you!
[Sanzo] I don't think so.
Pointed ears, a symbol
shamped birthmark...
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
and say your pumps a little bit
darker than mine.
[Sanzo] o you know what this is?
A banishing gun!
Well, it looks like word's
starting to get around.
You guys are a little more
organized than I thought
you were.
Alright then, if you know what
this then you know what it can
do. Right?
You've got ten whole seconds
to tell me who's violated the
forbidden tenent,
and who's responcible for this
bloody little uprising.
Too slow!
You said ten seconds, that was
only two!
I suck at math. Now tell me.
I swear to the goddess, I don't
know who's behind this! I don't
know what you're talking about!
I'm just following Kougaiji's
orders! I don't know anything!
Kougaiji?!
Gyumaoh and Rasetsunyo's son.
But when then Gyumaoh was put
down Kougaiji was supposed to
be sealed away in India,
Houtou Castle.
Who broke the seal and
freed him?
Whoever broke that seal,
whoever freed him, that's
who's behind this.
Who is it?
You sure you want to waste all
this time trying to figure
it out?
By the time you put it all
together your friends will
be dead!
That is if they're not
dead already.
Look you're being to generous in
assuming I care about their
safety that is.
They can take care of
themselves, I don't really
need to worry about- ugh!
[Spider] I suppose you should be
less concerned with your friends
and spend that time worry
about yourself.
[Sanzo] Houmei!
I understand you're headed west,
well there's been a change
of plans,
for you and your friends.
Now you're going south!
[Knock at the door]
Go away.
I was hoping for a little
warmer welcome.
Got room in that bed for two?
Yeah I think I can fit you in.
[Glass breaking]
A little noisy next door.
Not nearly as noisy as it's
going to be in here.
I can get pretty loud.
Not a problem.
[Gojoy] But I gotta ask you a
favor, can you maybe trim those
nails a little bit?
How did you know?!
I was told you'd be to busy
trying to get laid to figure
out who I was.
Sweetheart, when it comes to
my women...
...I'm picky.
That's pretty lame,
you did everything but knock
over a vase
to let me know you were coming.
[Gojyo] Hakkai, you alright?
Mine was a little better looking
at least.
[Hakkai] Whatever, did you
check Sanzo and Goku?
Goku's next door. We check on
him first.
Are you all right, Goku?!
What? I'm fine. I had the
weirdest dream.
More like a nightmare,
my friend.
He did this in his sleep?
That's bullshit.
I have to tell you, no one
has ever escaped from the
Dark Spider Clan.
Not even priests I'm afraid.
Black magic, illusions, I
should have seen her coming
a mile away.
I'm getting lazy.
Stop struggling and be a
good boy.
And I just might let this
girl live.
[Sanzo] You hurt her, you die.
[Spider] Such spirit, seems
wasted on a human.
Legend has it that if you
consume a priest of high
virtue, you'll live longer.
Prehaps one ranked as high
as Sanzo could provide life
ever lasting.
Give or take a decade or two.
To human women you must look
very handsome but to me,
you're dinner.
Up close like this you look
different, uglier.
I'll destroy you!
I'll tear you into such tiny
little pieces, you won't be ab-
I'd rethink the menu, honey.
That dish is a little sour.
I think she's bitten off more
than she can chew.
[Goku yawns]
[Sanzo] If you're looking for a
thank you, keep searching.
Wasn't really planning on it.
But would you like a little help
taking her down?
The more the merrier.
Go ahead and try it!
I'll spilt your little friend in
two before you take a step!
Hmm...
Sounds like a challenge to me.
You're too slow lady, and
now that we have your
barganing chip...
How about you just surrender and
give up?
Kill them all!
Come on! I'm ready to end
this bullshit!
Cause I'm sick of looking at
your ugly ass!
Nice job there, monkey boy.
Almost as nice as mine.
And now... my turn.
I'll kill you all one by one!
Well is that it? Huh?
Haven't you had enough?
Oh I'm just getting started!
Oh shit!
Oh she's chaning!
Eww! That's gross!
Yeah, kinda hard to tell which
one of her is uglier.
Augh! This is nasty! Get this
shit off me!
Her powers are increasing now
that she's changed into
another form.
Wow, you're awake.
By timing, my dear.
[Houmei screams]
We're free.
Houmei!
Dad!
Oh dad!
[Man] I believe this belongs
to you.
Well I guess I owe you a
finder's fee then.
[Spider] Oh you'll pay!
You'll all pay!
Houmei, don't look at it!
Oh god! She's eating
her friends!
She's healing her wounds by
consuming their power.
She likes to eat men.
She really is a spider.
Come here little girl!
[Goku] Back off!
[Houmei] Goku no!
Stop it! Why do you insist on
protecting them?! They're weak!
You are of my kind! We are
the same!
What?
That can't be! He- He can't be!
Goku, she's lying, right?
[Goku] What? Uh well, uh...
she's kinda on the level on
this one...
So she's tell the truth. Liar.
You liar! How could you lie to
me, knowing how I feel?!
Don't say that, Houmei!
Get away from me, you monster!
[Sanzo] Goku!
Everybody get back!
Stop this madness and join
forces with me!
We can rule the world with
Gyumaoh forever!
[Goku] Not interested!
And stop looking at them like
they're different or
we're better!
We're all the same! All of us!
Well, except for the little fact
that they cook better than I do.
I mean it, thanks.
Oh Goku...
A little help here, come on
you guys!
[Sanzo] Hakkai, take care of
Houmei and her father.
Gojyo, you help Goku, buy me
some time.
[Gojyo] Done.
A seal. Let's take her down.
Bring it on, spider lady!
You know, Houmei and her dad run
a really nice place here.
except for the pest problem.
[Houmei] Who are you?
What are you?
Houmei, the demons through out
the land
aren't doing these terrible
things for the thrill of it all.
Something is making them act
this way.
Some of them, anyway. You're
young becareful of blanket
judgements.
Now's your chance man,
go get her!
It's about time!
Now maybe she'll get me point!
[Man] Leaving so soon?
[Hakkai] Yes. We've got a long
way to go.
I guess Houmei's not coming to
see us off.
Probably not, not after
what happened yesterday.
You're a liar!
How could you do this me knowing
how I feel?! Liar! Liar!
[Houmei] Goku, wait!
Hey you're here!
It's not much. Just a little
something to say I'm sorry.
Goku, please forgive me if
you can.
I'm sorry, I was wrong about
you. Do you forgive me?
[Goku] Yeah!
Thank you!
Father, I was so wrong. Do you
think the others will be able to
forgive me?
Of course, but not until you're
able to forgive yourself.
It's hard to accept those who
are differnt from ourselves.
[Goku] And stop looking at them
like they're different or
we're better!
We're all the same! All of us!
[Man] Maybe one day we will all
be able to live as brothers.
You know what this means. They
know what are plans are.
Stop the resurrection, and this
Kougaiji guy.
Seems like we've got enemies
being freed and resurrected
all over the place.
[Gojyo] Yeah, this stuff
aint bad.
[Goku] Hey get your hands off!
[Sanzo] I'm sorry I can't
concentrate.
[Goku] This isn't for you!
[Gojyo] Like hell it's not!
[Gojyo] She gave it to all
of us!
[Sanzo] Not with those two
morons in the back.
[Goku] No she didn't! She gave
it to me!
I'm trying to ignore them.
[Sanzo] Really? How's it going?
[Hakkai] Not so good.
[Goku] Give it back!
That's mine!
[Gojyo] You know you're a real
selfish pain in the ass.
[Goku] Hahahaha! Suck it!
[Goku] OK, this is bullshit!
There's no meat,
there's no fish, we have to
bring our own beer!
This trip is getting worse
and worse!
Last time it's a hotel crawling
with demons, this time it's a
bunch of stuffy monks!
I don't know what's worse:
what's in here, or what's
out there.
[Gojyo] Shut up and tell 'em
the title.
[Goku] "His God, My God." Happy?
[Gojyo] Delirious.