Well I'll be. I hate to tell
you this, but that guy's
still following us.
Look, just keep walking.
I'm just saying.
[Sanzo] Will you just shut
up and walk?
Okay...
You realize I will always
be grateful to you for
saving my life.
Perhaps this is my act
of penitence.
The crimson color of your hair
and eyes reminds me of...
...the color of all the blood
I have spilled.
The crimson that stains my hands
is what keeps me grounded
in reality,
even as I attempt to escape
the weight of my sins.
Your hair and your eyes
are the only things that
admonish me, Gojyo.
Remember that.
I'm such a... an asshole.
[Gojyo] Wake up, slowpoke!
[Goku] Bastard! Come back here!
Idiots.
Just you wait, Cho Gonou.
This hair and these eyes may
just be able to save you one
more time.
I won't let you down.
"An Ode to the Living"
My wound has opened again.
I don't know why I'm surprised.
I hope Gojyo is okay.
I caused him trouble all the
way to the very end.
I don't know why I brought
the gun with me.
I suppose it's too late
to return it now.
Kanan...
Kanan, if I could...
If I could only hold your body
in my arms...
What is... That's...
[Crowman] That's my older
brother, and you killed him!
I've been looking for you,
Cho Gonou!
So that I could give you this!
What is it?
Nothing.
At least I hope it was.
[Goku] Sanzo, are you sure this
is the right direction?
I think I can make a fairly
educated guess as to where
Cho Gonou's headed.
I'm betting Hyakugan
Maoh's place
Hyakugan Maoh?
It's where Cho Gonou
committed his mass murder.
Hey...
So what'll happen to him if
you catch him?
You seem quite devoted to him.
I did go through all that
trouble of saving his life,
you know.
It would be such a waste
to have him die.
[Sanzo] I don't know how Cho
Gonou will be dealt with either.
The Sanbutsushin have sole
authority over that.
[Gojyo] Hey...
A high ranking monk like
yourself should know
what I am.
From the color of my hair
and eyes alone.
[Sanzo] You're a half-breed.
Born of the unholy union between
man and demon.
It is said their children have
crimson eyes and hair.
Eyes the color of blood.
He said he found penitence
in these eyes.
I won't let you kill him.
Even if this is just my vanity,
I won't let you kill him!
This is so stupid.
Excuse me?
[Sanzo] What are you getting
out of this?
I don't care how you
were concieved.
Do you seriously believe that
the only red thing in the
entire world is blood?
If you do, then you may as well
just shave your head right now.
I know a temple you can join.
I believe I'll pass.
[Gojyo] Ow! You stupid monkey!
That hurts!
Aw, your hair's cold after all.
What?
Your hair's so red,
I thought you'd be burning up.
But it's not hot at all.
You're just a fake.
What are you getting
out of this?
I let my hair grow long,
and now I'm trying to save
someone who needs me.
But the one who wants to be
saved is me.
[Sanzo] What's wrong, Goku?
[Goku] I smell blood.
Which direction?
[Goku] Let's see... This way!
[Sanzo] Let's hurry!
[Crowman] Do you remember
the dead faces
of my clan, that you murdered?
Do you remember the look in the
eyes of my family as you drove
in your blade?
We of the Dark Crow had no
quarrel with you,
it was Hyakugan Maoh who forced
us to abduct your lover.
The sacrifice of one woman,
could have saved us!
But you selfishly killed
them all for the sake of
your revenge!
Now I seek revenge of my own!
Let's see if you think
your woman was worth
all this bloodshed.
Once you get a small taste
of what my clan has suffered!
[Cho] So, you wish to have your
revenge that badly, eh?
Well right then, fine, it's
not a life I would miss
that much anyway.
I'll make a deal with you.
First I'll give you my
right eye.
After that, you can have
my left.
Then my ear.
The my nose...
Then my face...
[Goku] Stop it!
[Goku] Your eye! Is your eye...
What on earth were
you thinking?!
There's absolutely nothing
wrong with your eyes!
I heard that you believe that
red was the color of penitence.
Penitence to what? The gods?
The gods do not save anyone.
You alone are responcible for
saving your life.
You could kill yourself if you
want to escape that way.
Killing yourself will not
accomplish anything.
But there are some things you
can do if you're still alive.
[Crowman] Who the hell are you?!
His friends?!
[Gojyo] No...
If you want to kill him, well
then you go right ahead.
But I should warn you that,
those who take it apon
themselves to kill others
have to be prepared to have
others try to kill them
in return.
That's what they call the law
of consequences. my friend.
It was some cranky old monk that
once told me that.
Don't mess with my head!
These demons can be such
bird brains.
Can you walk?
[Cho] I can manage.
[Sanzo] Hey!
You are going, right?
Hyakugan Maoh's castle.
[Goku] Here!
It's yours, isn't it?
Kanan...
[Sanzo] Let's go!
Yes sir.
I am in your debt.
My god...
This was Hyakugan Maoh's castle.
It's been torched by someone,
just a couple days ago.
I doubt anyone survived.
[Cho] I see.
Yet again, I wasn't able
to save her.
Hey, chant the sutra for
her, you dumb monk.
I doubt doing a chant would
ease his conscience any.
That stuff's not really about
being logical, you know?
I don't chant sutras for
the dead.
You got that?
[Gojyo] Sazno spoke in a
voice so clear it dispeled
any and all doubt.
And it seemed for a moment...
...we could all see again as we
gathered around this golden,
luminous light.
What is this?
[Monk] But...
It's all right. Please put
them on me.
[Sanbutsushin A] Priest Sanzo...
Sinner Cho Gonou...
You may now enter.
[Goku] Your hair's so red, I
thought you'd be burning up.
[Gojyo] They all just say
whatever they feel like.
[Sanzo] Do you seriously
believe that the only red thing
in the entire world is blood?
[Gojyo] Of course not,
I know that.
[Cho] They're an admonishment
to me.
[Gojyo] Then, I'll just
cut it off.
But the one who wants to be
saved is me.
It was some old monk who
once told me that.
[Gojyo] What are you saying?!
Cho Gonou is dead.
What are you talking about?!
Why'd you convince him not to
kill himself if you were going
to let him die?
I said the gods save no one.
No one is able to avoid the
fate they have chosen for
themselves.
No one can. Not even you.
[Gojyo] Man, that's the second
time a pretty face dumped me.
You are truly vain.
[Gojyo] Yeah, I guess I am.
[Woman A] Gojyo?
Yo!
[Woman C] What's up with
the haircut?
Oh, I needed a change.
I haven't seen you around
the bar lately.
I can't stay away.
Gambling is the only way I know
how to make a living.
[Woman A] Did you hook up
with someone?
[Woman C] What's going on?
Are you settling down?
Not this guy.
Though I did spend some time
with a tall, dysfunctional
blonde,
an impulsive excitable little
air head,
and I had an emotionally
unstable, head case
with a pretty face shack up with
me for awhle.
[gasps] What are you telling me?
[Gojyo] Later girls.
[All three] Oh, don't go,
Gojyo! Hey!
[Gojyo] Nothing's changed.
No matter how many times
I cut it,
my hair's still red when it
grows back.
And my eyes are always crimson
when I look in the mirror.
But I'm starting to be
okay with that.
Hey buddy, I'll take me
one of these.
[Clerk] You got it!
[Hakkai] They're a beautiful
red, aren't they, Gojyo?
[Gojyo] On second thought, I'll
take four of 'em.
I'll be damned! It's been
a while!
I'm afraid I was delayed.
What the hell happened to your
head? You look like a pirate!
You look like a chimp,
here have a few.
[Goku] Oh, thank you!
Hey, apples! Fantastic!
Dumb monk, what's the big idea?
You said he died.
[Sanzo] What're you
talking about?
What do you mean "What am I
talking about?"
Buddhism forbids taking a life.
He may be a criminal but you
didn't think we'd actually
kill him did you?
Just use your head.
I should kill you.
So, they did set you free, huh?
Uh-huh, though it wouldn't have
happened without Mr. Sanzo's
full support.
He was nice enough to interceded
with the Sanbutsushin,
to allow me to discard the
name of Cho Gonou and start
a new life.
Well then, what should I call
you from now on?
Hakkai, it's Cho Hakkai.
Cho Hakkai... Yeah, that fits
you much better than the old
one did!
You think so?
You sure that's not too much
for your puny monkey brain
to remember?
I can too remember!
It's Hakkai! Hakkai!
Hakkai! Hakkai! Hakkai! Hakkai!
Hakkai! Hakkai!
You know I think Goku's
on to something.
Say it a few more times and he
might actually have it down.
How many?
Thousand.
So, what do you have planned for
your new life?
Gojyo and I get alone all right,
so I thought I might room with
him for a little while.
Besides the poor guy can't even
remember what day they come to
pick up the trash.
He'd be absolutely hopeless
without me.
[Sanzo] Try living with a chimp.
[Gojyo] You shut up!
[Hakkai] It's funny.
[Goku] Don't tell me what to do,
[Goku] you purple head
shit head!
[Hakkai] I've sought death for
so long.
[Gojyo] Okay, that's it!
[Gojyo] Now you're gonna get it!
[Hakkai] But now...
There's nothing more valuable
in this world to me than life.
Hakkai, I just got your new
name memorized,
so you better not change it!
All right.
So? Is this haircut suppose to
be a way of putting your past
behind you?
Not really, I'm probably just
the same as him.
Engaged in a futile struggle.
Life is basically a futile
struggle until you die anyway.
Problem?
Does the look suit me?
Anything's better than that
nasty long hair.
[Gojyo] Then it's settled,
I'll grow it out again.
Shouldn't take too long.
[Sanzo] Are you trying to
pick a fight?!
All right!
What?!
What do you say we all go eat?
[Goku] Ahaha! You said it!
Food! Food!
[Sanzo] You're so noisy.
Will you shut up?
Can we go, Sanzo?
Are you kidding? There's no
way that-
You better be treating.
[Hakkai] Oh, what
wonderful weather!
[Gojyo] Perfect day for
a field trip, eh?
[Hakkai] There you go, let's
make it a picnic.
[Goku] Sanzo, are the bananas
for snack time?
[Sanzo] Will you cut it out? I
wouldn't go on a trip with you
fools if you paid me.
[Gojyo] That's what Sanzo said
three years ago,
and we're still driving.
You're probably able to rest
easier now that the rain has
let up, eh Sanzo?
What makes you think I would?
You're the one who gets uneasy
every time it's raining.
Yes that's true.
So tell me, why do you guys
hate rain so much?
Is there something you two
aren't telling me?
Come on! I want to know. What is
it? What is it? Huh?
[Goku] Ow! What was that for?!
[Sanzo] Shut up!
[Gojyo] Sit down and shut up.
You're not old enough to
understand yet.
[Goku] What are you
talking about?
[Gojyo] See? I told you.
[Gojyo] I guess the best way
to put it is we're stuck with
each other.
Our origins, our missions,
our past. None of that
really matters.
We're just living, so that one
day we can die laughing.
And it's not looking as if this
little fieldtrip of ours is
going to be ending anytime soon.
[Goku] When we meet a mysterious
lady in the desert,
she leads us to the village
of Tofugai.
But when we arrive we find out
that it's an abandoned
ghost town!
Not to mention the weird demon
shaped statues sitting around
everywhere.
Hey wait a second! Why are my
feet turning to stone!
What's going on here?! Does
that woman have something
to do with this?
Find out next time on Saiyuki
in "Eternal Paradise".