[Ni] I see why you're
so cold, Dr. Huang.
You get all your
sexual gratification
from your computer.
Where else would I find it?
Are you going to tell me
what's in the box or what?
Just something my brain came up
to play with people's hearts.
If they do have them.
[Goku] "Blood Bond."
[Gojyo] Finally. I thought
we'd never get there.
[Goku] And you know
what that means. Food!
[Hakkai] I'm afraid it's
not dinner time yet, but our
legs could all use a stretch.
[Goku] Please! I'm
dying over here!
[Gojyo] You, dying of hunger?
That I'd like to see.
What's wrong? Goku?
Goku!
I'll go get you some
food right away!
Just hold on! Don't
die on me, monkey!
In that case, I'll
take some pot stickers!
[Huang] Dr. Ni...
I admit that you
are a great scientist,
perhaps even one of the
greatest in the world...
Hear that, bunny?
She really likes us.
[Huang] But we are in the
service of Lady Gyokumen Koushu.
To act on our own would be...
Is it true you were
class president of
your elementary school?
I don't understand.
A bull's eye.
A spring of knowledge
that bubbles up in a
desert of incompetence,
chaos, and ignorance,
[Ni] will eventually be
swallowed up by the dry sand.
[Huang] Pardon?
Even if a single woman should
try desperately to drink some
of that superior knowledge,
that spring would have to
conserve some of it's water
for all the others who
are dying of thirst.
Oh, for crying out loud!
Are you the spring
in this scenario?
[Ni] All I'm saying is that
I don't want to be sucked into
the desert without reason.
May I present my queen bee.
A little hobby I've been
working on during my off hours.
You aren't intending to
use that on Genjo Sanzo...
without proper approval?
Are you always such
a fuddy-duddy?
Okay! It's time for you to go
round up your worker buddies.
Bye-bye.
[Hakkai] Bad news. It doesn't
look like this inn serves meals.
[Goku] What?!
[Hakkai] A drought has
apaprently put this village
into a nasty famine.
Hey, Gojyo. Why don't you
make yourself useful and
get us something to eat.
What? And why me?!
[Sanzo] Didn't I hear you tell
Goku a little while ago that
you'd go get us some food?
[Goku] Yeah!
But only because that
little monkey tricked me!
[Sanzo] A real man never
goes back on his word.
You're serious.
So long, Gojyo.
[Gojyo] Fine, I'll do it.
And you're going with me!
Man, I tell you. This
place is one big hellhole.
[Yanming] Please, just
a little? That's all I ask!
[Shopkeep] Go home! I have
nothing I'm willing to sell
to the likes of you!
[Yanming] But I could give you
this! Please! It's all I have-
[Shopkeep] GET OUT!
I'd sooner give food to the
dogs than sell any to you!
I beg you! Please help me!
[Gojyo] Hey, Mister, that's
no way to woo a lady.
You get-!
Your hair... The
color... of your eyes...
[Goyjo] Huh?
[Shopkeep] Here! Go!
What the...?
It looks like it's
free today, beautiful.
Truth now. Are my looks
that intimidating?
Yeah, like you're
after something.
Ah, dammit. Was I
thought obvious?
[Goku] What now?
I guess we just move on.
[Ni] Oh, very nice!
This village is a virtual
hotbed of hatred and fear.
My kind of town.
[Goku] There's gotta
be some place around
here with some food.
I'm famished!
[Goyjo] Get a hold of
yourself, will ya?
What is it?
I'll be. That lady again.
Do I still look intimidating?
You do.
Sweet.
I'm sorry for how
I acted before.
No biggie. Though I'm not use
to chicks running away from me.
When I saw you, I was so
stunned. I wasn't able
to think very clearly.
You know, I felt the
exact same way when I
saw your beautiful eyes.
What's your name?
Yanming...
Well Yanming, call me Gojyo.
Jeez. Get a room
for crying out loud.
[Yanming] Burning red...
the color of...
A mongrel birth.
Your hair and eyes betray
the forbidden union of
one parent human,
the other demon.
[Shopkeep] I tell
you, I saw him!
[Innkeep] That witch
has brought in others?!
We can't allow this to happen!
There's no telling
what they'll do!
Half-breeds!
Go gather the others.
[Shopkeep] Don't you
have any customers?
[Innkeep] Just a shady
monk and his party.
Nothing to worry
about. Let's go!
You think something happened?
Who knows? They sure are taking
their sweet time about it.
Knowing Gojyo, he's probably
using Goku to pick up women.
He'd be better off
with a dog. Woof.
I'm so starving.
[Hakkai] What do you
know? Welcome back.
[Sanzo] Where's Gojyo?
[Gojyo] So, it had nothing to do
with my piercing good looks, eh?
I'll get over it.
[Yanming] I'm sorry, but
seeing you did give me hope
my child could grow
up to be respectable.
Respectable, huh? Yeah.
I don't know about that.
I am alive, I suppose.
And that's something.
So, where's the boyfriend, huh?
Things were fine,
until one day, he...
he just changed into a madman!
[Gojyo] So it's the
same here too.
One day, he just left.
And that's the last
we ever saw of him.
I'm... I just really don't
know why. At first, the
others were kind to me.
And they told me
it wasn't my fault.
But I was with child...
And I knew there was no
way they could accept him.
A baby with eyes
as red as the sunset.
But I also knew that... that I
could never give up such a...
beautiful, beautiful child.
[Gojyo] I can't stand
to see a woman cry.
Everytime my mother
saw me, she cried too.
Why not just leave?
I can't. I've never known
any place else.
Besides, I must wait for him.
[Innkeep] There she is!
[Shopkeep] I told you
if we let her stay here,
others would follow!
[Innkeep] They're not
welcome here.
I wonder what they want?
[Gojyo] Oh boy, this
sure brings me back.
[The townspeople
mutter in disgust]
I'll be...
the perfect intersection
of sorrow and hatred.
Hurry, queen bee.
Show them your sting.
Hungry...
I think Gojyo's set
a new record.
His relationships
never last this long.
Let's go. I'm out of cigarettes.
[Innkeep] She's
improving. At least now
she's dating half humans.
[Villager] Show them a little
kindness, and they take
advantage of you!
[Shopkeep] We won't make
that mistake again!
What a bunch of assholes.
You're all wrong! He's
not here because of me!
[Innkeep] We're not going
to fall for it, demon lover!
[Villager] We won't let
you run us out of town!
Ever since you gave
birth to that monster,
our village hasn't seen
a single drop of rain!
Our wells dried up!
Nearby villagers are too afraid
of the curse of the red-eyed
baby to come near us!
This is all because of you!
But you've got it all wrong!
It's not you, disasters are
happening all around Shangri-La.
[Villager] Like we're going to
believe a demon spawn like you!
[Gojyo] Real bright, numb-nuts.
[Innkeep] You going to fight
or what?! Enough talk!
[Villager] Get out
of our village!
Stop it! What have we ever
done to hurt you?!
You see, sorrow is hatred my
pet. Two sides of a coin.
Release the pain that's
festering in you.
What's going on, Yanming?
What is it? What?
Yanming!
I feel as if I have been reborn.
Huh?!
Yanming!
[Villager] What is it?!
So she really was a
demon, a monster.
You will pay for what
you have done to me!
Yanming, that's enough!
No it's not!
Eat this, you bitch!
Idiots! Cease fire!
Dammit!
Goku, stop!
Where's my dinner, you slut?
Can I bum a smoke?
If you're through
cracking jokes,
I could use a little help.
[Goku] Hey! Is that the
same woman from before?!
Gojyo, what's happening?!
I don't know, but she must be
human because I never sensed
any kind of demon
aura coming from her.
Mess with me and
I'll destroy you too!
Sounds fun, lady!
Wanna wrastle?
[Gojyo] Stay out of this!
Listen! Attacking the
villagers isn't going to
solve your problems!
Demon halfbreed!
You more than anybody
should know the kind of
existence in store
for a mongrel!
A baby?
[Sanzo] So that's it?
That baby is the reason
for their hatred of me!
If only he never existed!
If he never existed!
You know that isn't true !
Gojyo, what're you doing?!
Sanzo!
Out of the way!
[Gojyo] Stop it! I've suffered
enough for the two of us!
No mother ever thinks
their own child is ugly.
Isn't that right?!
Gojyo, please. I...
[Gojyo] Isn't that
right, Yanming?
[Yanming] Please run, Gojyo!
[Gojyo] Yanming.
[Yanming] There's nothing
I can do anymore!
Don't be stupid!
[Yanming] I don't
want to hurt my baby!
But I can't control my hatred!
My body has a will of its own!
That's it!
[Gojyo] You can fight it!
[Yanming] I... I...
I will kill everyone who
tries to stand in my way.
[Gojyo] Oh no.
Gojyo! So what do we do?
We have to kill her!
[Gojyo] Stay out of this!
I won't let you hurt her!
Yanming is the only
mother he has!
I won't let this baby
suffer the way I suffered!
Who else would take care
of a mongrel baby like this,
if not his own mother?
His own mother!
Nice try!
Look out!
What's happening?!
I can't tell...
[Goku] Gojyo!
[Goku] Gojyo! Are
you alright? Gojyo!
It's okay. He's alive.
So you did notice it.
Looks like it.
Am I the only one who
hasn't figured out
what's going on here?
Look here.
This is what has been
controlling Yanming.
[Goku] Oooh.
[Hakkai] By luring her to
attack him, it provided Gojyo
with the opportunity
to grab it from her neck.
That's so smart!
I have to agree. It goes to
show you, you can't judge
a book by its cover.
Non-perishables go there.
Aye, aye, miss president.
And please stop calling me that!
[Gojyo] Guess this
is goodbye, beautiful.
[Goku] Are you going
to be alright by yourself?
I won't ever be alone.
Not if I have him.
Are you sure now? It's
a harsh world out there.
[Yanming] Maybe so, but the
best way to prepare him for
that is to be strong myself.
What kind of mother would I
be if I taught him to be afraid?
I'm sad to be leaving my
village, but it would be best
for my son if I find his father.
[Goku] You realize
that in Shangri-La...
Push come to shove, and I'll
turn into the bee woman again.
Huh? Those stingers really hurt.
I'm sorry.
[Koushu] Ni! I know
you're around here!
Yes, Lady Gyokumen Koushu?
There you are.
[Ni] You're always in
my thoughts, My Lady.
I'm bored, Ni. So bored.
[Ni] My, that IS a
problem now, isn't it?
Do you have something
to amuse me?
Uh... I'm afraid I have
not time for frivolities
since I devote myself to
serving you, your highness.
Well then, I have
a favor to ask you.
I'm feeling a little parched.
Then I'll go fetch
you something.
[Koushu] Yes, this dry desert of
ignorance would love a chance to
lap at your fountain.
Thirsty girl.
[Goku] It seems like someone's
always trying to kill us.
So what else is new? But there's
something different about this
new group of assassins on
our tail. I get the feeling t
hat they're bad news.
Hey, you guys, can
we fight 'em? Okay?
Next time on Saiyuki, we
face "The Mightiest Foe."