Uh, sorry.
[Kenren] Golden eyes...
[Goku] See ya!
[Kenren] Wait a sec.
What didja go and do that for?!
You wouldn't happen to be
the Goku that Tenpou was
talking about, would you?
Wha... What, are you a good
friend of Tenpy's, mister?
I'm no mister! I'm not that old.
General Kenren!
[Kenren] Hm?
[Subordinate 2] General Kenren.
[Subordinate 2] That child
has been wandering through
the Emperor's castle
without permission.
There's no telling
how he got in here.
[Kenren] It's okay.
He's with me.
[Subordinate 2] What?
So you know him, General?
[Kenren] You could say that...
He's my bastard son.
[Both] Son?
[Kenren chuckles, amused]
[Goddess] Things that
don't change are so lame.
[Goku] "Defying the Gods."
[Kenren] Why'd you
sneak in there anyway?
The castle's not connected
to the Goddess's palace.
Well, that's where I met my new
bestest friend in the whole
world, Nataku, the other day.
[Kenren] Nataku?
[Goku] Yeah! I came
back to look for him.
Hey, wait a minute.
You can't mean the
War Prince Nataku.
Mmhmm! That's him, alright!
Now that I finally
got myself a name,
I wanted to tell
him what it was.
'Cause it's a really cool one!
[Kenren] Whaddya know?
The puppet assassin
has a friend.
What?
[Kenren] Oh, nothing.
Nataku's kind of busy right now.
[Goku] He's not here?
[Kenren] He's got stuff
to do in the Lower World.
He should be back in a few days.
[Goku] I'll come by then.
Oh man, you are really heavy.
[Goku] Huh? Oh, yeah.
That's 'cause I have these on.
[Kenren] Wow.
These manacles as
heavy as boulders,
yet he moves around
like they're nothing.
How dangerous does this kid
have to be to warrant such
drastic measures?
[Kenren] You're something else.
[Subordinate] General Kenren!
[Kenren] What's up?
[Subordinate] Prince Nataku
has just returned from
the Lower World!
What? Really?
There a problem?
[Subordinate] No, Nataku
defeated Gyumaoh...
But I'm afraid the battle
has taken it's toll on him.
[Attendant] Are you
all right, Lord-
Hands off!
[Goku] Nataku!
Nataku, are you alright?
Nataku!
You're the... guy I met...
[Goku] Nataku!
Nataku!
Hey, Tenpou.
Daydreaming again, eh Tenpou?
You there, Tenpou?
Sheesh, I just helped you
organize this place a month ago.
Hey! Where are you?
Hello.
[Kenren] "Hello?" That all
you have to say after all the
times I called out to you?
[Tenpou] Augh, sorry.
I guess I didn't hear you.
[Kenren] I was screaming
at the top of my lungs.
[Tenpou] I must have gotten
absorbed in this book on
the military history
of the Lower World.
This is amazing. You would
think that peace would
not be possible,
for a race that refuses
to believe in ideology.
But they seem to have
found their own way.
I do believe this strange race
has stumbled upon a way to
achieve a balance.
[Kenren] You know, I don't
think it's possible for
me to care any less.
Oh?
Thought you should know,
Nataku is back from his mission.
That sure didn't take very long.
I mean, after all the
administration's hand wringing.
Looks to me like the great
Prince Nataku didn't exactly
escape unscathed this time.
They say he's unconscious.
There's one thing that
still bothers me...
about those soldiers.
Every one of them came
back without so much
as a scratch on them.
Meaning they all just stood
by and watched the battle?
That bothers me too.
Hm, by the way, I happened
to run into that little
pipsqueak friend of yours.
[Tenpou] Oh? Goku?
[Kenren] That's the first
time I've seen golden eyes,
yet that little monkey didn't
seem much like a heretic to me.
He acted like such a
harmless little goofball.
Are those shackles
really necessary?
Immortals don't really care very
much for heretics, now do they?
You know the real reason they
chain him, only because they
can't eliminate him.
In that sense, he's very
much like Prince Nataku.
[Old God] You are a heretic!
[Nataku's mother] How could
I have given birth to such
a horrible monster?!
It's disgusting!
[Touten] You were
born only to fight.
No one will grieve if you die.
Stop it! Stop it!
JUST STOP IT!
[Goku] Nataku!
[Nataku] Huh?!
Good, you're awake!
[Nataku] It's you...
[Goku] I was starting to wonder
if you'd ever wake up at all.
You alright, Nataku?
Yeah.
I guess...
I remember battling Gyumaoh...
Now I'm here.
Jerks. Look at this place!
You fight that guy,
then they go and stick
you in a place like this?
It's like a prison!
[Nataku] It's okay.
I'm expendable.
No one cares what happens to me.
[Goku] And just what's
that suppose to mean?
I certainly don't think so.
I'm here, aren't I?
You're the only person who
hasn't treated me like
some kind of heretic.
I mean, you even like the
fact that I'm different
than everybody else.
I see.
Let's say, as soon as I'm
healed and feeling better,
I'll show you around some.
I know lots of good
places to hide,
where we can pick berries
or whatever you want.
I'm there!
That would be just great!
You don't look so good.
Uh... I'll go get someone.
Huh?
Please don't go. I'll be fine.
Lord Konzen, I humbly
beg your forgiveness.
I'm sorry, we had no
idea you were his guardian.
I'm not his guardian.
I'm his owner.
[Attendant] What?
[Konzen] Sorry if he troubled
you. I'll take him home.
[Konzen] Hey, monkey,
get your butt over here.
Oh great.
Now there's two of them.
[Goku] Hey, Konzen.
What are all those people out
there for? What are they doing?
It's a festival... for
the Jade Emperor's birthday.
A festival?
Believe me, it's not
as fun as it sounds.
I've got an idea, why don't you
just stay here for tonight?
Do what you want.
[Goku] Yaaaaaay! A festival!
[Goku yells in frustration]
[Konzen] Damn it!
What the hell is it now?!
My name! I totally forgot to
tell Nataku my name yesterday!
And after all that trouble too!
What's the problem?
Can't you just tell him
the next time you see him?
You're buddies, right?
Yeah! That's right!
[Touten] Do you think
we're in any danger?
[Administrator 1] It is true,
there have been some grumblings
of dissatisfaction with
the administration.
[Administrator 2] They are
only rumors at this point.
I don't believe it's gone too
far up the chain of command.
But it could interfere
with our plan.
[Touten] Fine, dispose of them
as soon as you've located
these conspirators.
[Administrator 2] As you wish.
[Administrator 1] I think Nataku
could be a problem for us.
He is unusually disobedient.
[Touten] Like all good warriors,
he is somewhat brash
and arrogant.
And headstrong at times.
But he would never
dare oppose my will.
He is a dutiful son.
Wow, so cool!
This little soiree is the most
popular festival we have.
You could get lost in a crowd.
Which means, don't wander off!
[Yawning loudly]
Merciful Goddess,
someone might see you!
But I'm so freaking bored.
Do you think I want to
be at this old geezer's
birthday party?
I've got better things
to do with my time.
He's immortal,
for crying out loud.
The only reason we have to
be here is to demonstrate our
loyalty to him, year after year.
And what's that prove,
since attendance is
mandatory anyway?
Ah! But then again, this year...
Lady?
We might get a shake up
of the same old routine.
[Merciful Goddess chuckles]
[Goku] Huh?
Where's Konzen?
Attention! Attention!
May I have your
attention, please!
Goku, don't you even think
about talking during the
Emperor's speech.
Now where the hell did he...
run off to this time?!
[Nataku] Look at
all those posers.
Acting like they
want me to be there.
It disgusts me.
[Touten] You look bored, Nataku.
Uh, no. I'm just tired,
that's all... father.
Listen son, I want
you to know something.
One day, I will be
the Jade Emperor.
And you will be my
shining successor.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Well?
[Nataku] Yes, father.
[Nataku] Sometimes...
I see danger looming
in my father's eyes.
I have ruled a period
of unprecedented peace.
But now I must call on you
to destroy the demon race!
Heaven needs your service!
Oh man, where did he go now?
I bet he's really
gonna be mad at me.
Maybe he's over this way.
[Attendee 1] Now who let
this animal off it's leash?
You should watch where
you're going, punk.
What the hell? You're the
one who ran into me, you jerk!
[Attendee 2] What?
[Attendee 1] Hey look.
The boy has golden eyes.
Yeah, you're right.
So this is the guy.
[Attendee 1] Yes it is. That
vile heretic they dug up from
the lower world. Disgusting.
[Attendee 2] You know,
for as much of an antisocial
hermit as Konzen is,
he sure dotes over this creature
like an old mother hen.
I think we may have
finally found out why
he doesn't like women.
He likes little boys!
[Attendee 1 laughs]
Did you just say something
bad about my friend, Konzen?
I won't let you get
away with that!
Now take it back, right now!
You'll pay for this!
Don't tell me this
is the way you always
discipline little boys.
[Goku] Hey! Tenpy!
Wh-why aren't you...
Well, if it isn't that
Field Marshal Tenpou.
You two might try
growing up some,
rather than going around
picking on little children,
who are half your size.
Ha! Those are awfully big
words for a foot soldier.
What's all of this ruckus?!
Who in the name of the
Heavens dares to disrupt
the Emperor's speech?
[Soldier 1] One side, one side!
[Soldier 2] Out of the way!
Alright now! What the hell
is all this racket about?!
What's this!? Get rid of
this disgusting creature!
On the double!
[Soldier 2] Yes, Sir!
[Goku] Ugh! Don't touch me!
Moron!
Catch that runt!
Wait, that child is...
[Soldier] Hyah!
Take that.
Okay, that was funny.
Kenren...
This looks like a lot more
fun than that boring speech.
May I join you?
Oooh boy. Looks to me like
things just took a big
fat turn for the worse.
Even a four-star general would
be punished for this moral
outrage and disrespect!
Heh. Believe me, I should be
rewarded for disrupting
that boring old thing.
So, come on guys!
If you've been wanting a piece
of me, here's your chance.
[Kenren chuckles]
[Tenpou] You just had to
rile them up, didn't you?
[Attendee 1] Get him!
It's about damn time too!
[Kenren laughs]
This is too much fun.
You've sure made a lot of
enemies lately, haven't you?
You realize...
that they only hate me because
I happen to work with you.
Oh? I'm sorry, I didn't
realize it was like that.
In that case...
I'll lend you a hand.
[Goku] Nailed him...
Wow, what a punch!
These guys are awesome!
Uh oh!
Look out, Tenpy!
Whoo! Not bad for
a little monkey.
Don't call me a monkey!
[Jade Emperor continues
with his speech]
[Attendant 1] Quiet down there!
We are trying to listen!
[Emperor] -in the name of
peace, we must root them out!
[Gojun] Him again.
[Touten] What is it?
[Lady] My lord, I'm afraid
something appears to be causing
a commotion in the square.
[Nataku] It's him!
[Touten] Disgusting.
It disturbs me to hear
of men of such poor and
degenerate characteristics.
Don't you agree, Nataku?
[Nataku] Yes, father.
[Nataku] Freedom lies just
beyond this railing...
and I am too weak
to reach for it.
Hey! What's all this racket?!
Do you hear me?! Be quiet!
[Merciful Goddess chuckles]
See, Jiroushin? Don't
you find this amusing?
I cannot help but feel
sorry for the Emperor.
Oh, I think he'll survive.
Fire and fights will be
the highlights of Edo.
To be honest, madam,
I've never heard of it.
[Konzen] Goku! Goku!
What did you do
this time, monkey?!
[Kenren] Hm?
[Tenpou] Ah! Looks like
your owner's arrived.
Hey, Konzen!
Ah ha.
So this is the guy, huh?
[Konzen] Dammit!
I told you to stay close!
[Goku] I didn't mean to!
Hey, give the kid a break.
Kids tend to wander off.
Hey, that happens.
Don't touch me!
Now who are you?
I'm the unruly General.
The one with no command of
his groin or his liquor.
So you're Kenren. Hmph.
There you are, my lord Konzen!
I was so very worried when
I couldn't find you at
your appointed seat!
Please return to
your place at once!
[Konzen] Hmph.
[Attendant] Huh?
I fear these three are with me,
so it looks like you'll
have to throw all four
of us out of this party.
[Attendant] B-b-b-but, sir...
Let's go.
This was our fault.
You don't need to be tied
up with us, you're innocent.
Hmph. On the bright side,
at least now I don't
have to be here.
[Gojun] These four
are dangerous...
[Goddess] Haha. Now you've
gone and done it, Konzen.
You'll be tied up with
these three misfits
for some time to come.
I can't wait to see what
kind of trouble you'll cause.