He doesn't seem... to
act like he's fighting.
It's like... he's really
enjoying himself.
Sanzo...
What would you say...
...if you could see this?
Damn it!
Kou!
[Goku] "The Battle Ends"
I don't... stand a chance.
Not against a monster like him.
This is no joke.
He defeated Dokugakuji
with just one kick.
This is insane.
I fear... the insane
part is about to begin.
Any idea how to stop him?
Stop him? Oh brother.
What were you thinking, Goku?
All right, monkey. Let's
get this over with.
Not again!
Now I'm really angry!
Stop... acting like
you're... enjoying it...
Look. That's enough now, Goku.
Sanzo was poisoned a half
hour ago. He'll die if
we don't help him soon.
The only one who's going
to be hurt if you don't
stop this rampage...
is you, Goku.
I'm not getting through
to him. Uh-oh.
Goku!
It's taking everything I've
got just to dodge him.
Gojyo, get his coronet! Quick!
Gojyo...
Who are we kidding?
He's just too much.
What the hell is that thing?
Whatever it is, it's no demon.
It's a monster.
Yes, but it's still Goku.
[Hakkai] Goku...
[Gun fires]
Pull yourself together,
you stupid monkey.
Sanzo!
It can't be. He's
lucky to even be alive.
Moving around like that
would just make the
poison spread quicker.
Go ahead. Kill me
if you can. Try it.
You wouldn't...
Come on.
I'm afraid I've got
no bullets to waste on
you, you damn monkey.
[Sanzo] Return now
to your human form.
[Hakkai] He's
returned to normal.
Stupid chimp...
Neither of them look too good.
[Dokugakuji] Kou!
Wake up, Kou! Oh no.
Is he all right?
[Dokugakuji] As much as I'd
to finisht his, I am going to
withdraw for the time being.
I know we've been enemies,
but I mistook you guys
for men of honor.
This wasn't about who had
the better skill, but who
could tear the other down.
so I'll admit...
We lost this fight.
But know that I will never
forgive you for this.
No, I suppose you won't.
Hakuryu, I see you're
feeling better.
If you don't mind, could you
turn back into our jeep?
Many thanks. Where
would we be without you?
Pathetic, isn't it, Kou?
First we lose the fight.
Then I renege on your bet
by taking the flying
dragon anyway.
I'm afraid... we have no choice
friend. If you live, you can
complain to me all you want to.
[Hakkai] Hang in there, Hakuryu.
Sanzo's in even worse shape
than you are little buddy.
Best thing for both
of you, is to reach the
village before sundown.
[Hakuryu cries in response]
My vision's getting blurry. I
might be bleeding internally.
I'm not sure if I can make it.
Gojyo?
Let me drive, Hakkai.
[Hakkai] Please, go lie down.
You're in no condition to
do anything. Look at you.
Hold on.
Just go.
Gojyo...
[Gojyo] Don't go pulling
those kind of heroics
to show off, hear me?
Makes me feel so pathetic.
[Hakkai] It's all yours.
[Renli] So what if
you are a Sanzo?!
In the end, you're just a weak
human who chants silly sutras!
Maybe I am.
Hey! What're you doing, Sanzo?!
[Gojyo] I don't think I've
ever seen you so brutal.
It's not like me, eh?
What exactly am I like?
Go ahead. Strike me with
your stupid paper fan.
That's what the Sanzo
I know would do to me.
You just continue being
strong, Priest Genjo Sanzo.
[Sanzo] But I am not strong.
[Hakkai] We know that.
But that's not necessarily the
same thing as being weak, is it?
On that note, how
are you feeling?
I feel like shit.
I can't say that I'm surprised.
You were unconscious for three
whole days. I take the fact
that you're cursing again
as a positive sign, though.
Have I really been
out that long?
[Hakkai] After moving
around like you did with
a dose of lethal poison
coursing through your veins,
you're lucky you woke up at all.
You're a very fortunate man.
Truth is, none of us remember
how we got back to the village.
Lord knows, we would have
shriveled up out there in
the desert if that boy
hadn't found us when he did.
What happened to Kougaiji?
Dokugakuji carried
him back home.
But I fear he carried
a grudge with him.
To be honest, I can't say
I blame him for it though.
I see.
Listen to me, if you're
worried about Goku, he's
just in the other room.
C'mon. Was I wrong?
Who cares about him?
[Hakkai] I seem to remember
that you once told me you
never take any excess baggage
with you. Isn't that so?
My bad. Sorry.
I'll have you know, you're
quite a handful yourself,
Sanzo. So be that way.
When did you become
so... annoying?
Am I? I suppose, I'm
lashing out at you.
I didn't know what fear was
until I faced Goku in his
berserk mode. He had entrusted
me with bringing him back.
ME, but I was powerless to stop
him. I have never felt so weak.
But I can't help but be a
little bitter at myself for it.
What's worse... by letting him
down, the results of what he's
done will hurt him even more.
It's just so sad.
[Gojyo] Ow ow ow ow ow!
Dammit man, could you wrap
that thing any tighter?!
Stop your whining! You're
such a baby, I swear.
If it hurts so damn much, have
Hakkai do it next time! Sheesh.
You're the one who did
this to me so deal with
it, stupid monkey!
What's the big deal? It's not
like it was that serious anyway.
Your damn rampage broke
three of my ribs. If that's
not serious, then what is?
Huh?!
[Goku] I SAID I was sorry! Jeez!
It didn't make me feel any
better when you went and took
a quiet nap right afterwards,
as if nothing had happened.
[Goku] I'm sorry.
I feel... awful.
Oh man, I'm just giving
you a hard time.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I doubt we could have
saved Sanzo if you hadn't...
gone berserk like that.
Everything worked out okay.
Didn't it?
[Goku] I suppose...
But I...
can't remember what I did...
These hands... they nothing
else but the death of others.
And I don't just mean Kougaiji.
It could have been you
or Hakkai, or Sanzo.
I... could have killed you all.
What'd you do that for?!
Let's get something
straight, shall we?
There is no way you
could kill me, no matter
what form you take.
Whether you turn into your
long haired hippie demon
self, or some uglier monster.
You'll never beat me.
Never ever. You got that?
Besides, I've already decided
the why I'm gonna die.
And that's my friend, is in
the arms of some hot babe.
Do you understand me?
I'm not gonna let you or anybody
else keep me from that, got it?
You do that again and I will!
My goodness, do you
mind keeping it down?
I could hear you guys
all the way out here.
Sanzo... appears
to be awake now.
Well, then maybe we should
take a look at his ugly face.
Slow down, monkey.
Let me go! Let me go!
Sanzo's probably really pissed
at me now for what I did!
He's just gonna wop me
with his stupid fan again!
My word, you were pacing
around more anxiously than
any of us just a moment ago.
Yeah, but...
I think you'll find that
Sanzo is a little more
forgiving than that.
Probably...
Yeah but...
You don't really think you can
just run away, do you, Goku?
I guess not...
Uh, hey. What's up?
What do ya know? Your
owner's here, Goku.
He never behaves himself
this much when I'm
around, now does he?
[Sanzo] Goku...
Yes sir?
Could you possibly...
grab a beer for me?
[Goku] Uh, sure.
Here you go.
Thanks.
What were you thinking?!
Ow, my head!
Could you be anymore stupid?!
Aren't I always telling
you to think before act,
you stupid monkey!
Will you never learn?!
Hakkai, you said Sanzo would
be forgiving, but he isn't!
That's why I added
the "probably."
Oh man...
What are you giggling about?
I'm not giggling.
You're so creepy.
I think Sanzo's starting
to warm up a little.
He can be twisted at times
but... it's kind of nice
to see his feminine side.
I hope you don't mind.
I brought you guys some
fresh bandages here.
[Gojyo] You know you
can poke someone's eye
out with that thing!
[Sanzo] Only if they aren't
behaving themselves.
[Gojyo] You're one to talk
Mr. High-and-Mighty!
How very kind of you.
[Sanzo] Go ahead and try it.
[Gojyo] You know, maybe I
will-hey, what's the big idea?!
[Goku] I won't
let you hurt Sanzo!
Why you stupid monkey!
This doesn't concern you,
now step aside! NOW!
You bastard!
Go ahead and call me
a monkey all you want!
It's better than being a
big red roach like you!
[Gojyo] "Red roach?" Where
on earth did you come
up with that?!
[Goku] If you're not a
roach, then what are
those antennas for?
[Boy] You're friends are weird.
[Gojyo] OW! Stop pulling them!
Yeah, you're right, and you
don't know the half of it.
And for that, you
should be thankful.
[Dokugakuji] We made it, Kou.
Yaone will fix
you right up, man.
Welcome back.
[Hakkai] It hasn't been
easy, living when the one
dearest to me has died.
In her last breath, she said
she had forgiven me for not
being able to save her...
but I have not been
able to forgive myself.
So what would I do if I met
someone who reminded me of her?
Would I... could I...
Next time on Saiyuki,
I learn "The Price of Devotion."