[ HIDENORI TOKUYAMA'S
"STILL TIME" PLAYS ]
[ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-SO, LET'S BEGIN.
-[ GRUNTING ]
-THAT'S RIGHT, GOKU.
LET GO.
LET GO OF ALL YOUR RAGE,
ALL YOUR HUNGER.
LET YOURSELF BECOME THE SPARK
THAT IGNITES THE FORMATION
OF THE NEW HEAVEN AND EARTH.
YOU ARE THE CREATOR.
-[ SCREAMING ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
[ SCREAMING CONTINUES ]
-THAT'S GOOD, GOKU.
LET IT ALL OUT.
OHH!
[ GRUNTING ]
NOT YET.
I'M NOT --
NOT READY TO LET --
LET THIS LIFE END YET.
-STEP ASIDE.
-WHAT'S THE IDEA?
-THIS GUY, HE'S ALL MINE.
-NO NEED TO FIGHT OVER ME,
FELLAS.
I'LL TAKE YOU BOTH ON.
-I DON'T SHARE MY PREY.
-WE'LL SEE WHO'S THE HUNTER.
-PREPARE YOURSELF.
-HYAH!
-WILL YOU STOP THIS?
I HAVE NO WISH TO FIGHT
A WEAK LITTLE CHILD LIKE YOU.
RUN ALONG NOW.
-A CHILD, HUH?
DON'T YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME!
I CAN BE TOUGH WHEN I WANT TO.
-THAT'S TRUE.
THEN I SHALL FIGHT YOU
IN EARNEST.
-[ GRUNTING ]
[ MACHINE-GUN FIRE ]
-DON'T THINK I WON'T FIRE BACK!
AAH!
-CUTE TRICK.
WELL, WE DON'T APPEAR TO BE
GETTING ANYWHERE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE END THIS RIGHT NOW?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
AH, SURE.
WHAT THE HELL?
GO AHEAD AND SHOOT.
WHAT'S WRONG, SANZO?
YOU DIDN'T THINK
I'D PROTECT YOU, DID YOU?
-LIKE HELL.
[ MACHINE-GUN FIRE ]
-[ SQUEALS ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
-HOLD YOUR FIRE.
-I WAS WONDERING
WHERE YOU'D BEEN.
-DAMN.
JUST WHAT I NEED.
-SANZO, WHERE'S GOKU?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
-DON'T TELL ME YOU --
YOU DIDN'T!
-SHUT UP!
-WILL YOU CONTINUE TO BE
THE LITTLE TYKE'S SHINING SON,
SANZO?
-WHAT IS IT?
-WE'RE OUT OF TIME!
DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
LET'S GO FIND GOKU!
-GOJYO.
-WHAT?
-YOU TAKE CARE OF THIS.
-COME AGAIN?
-I'VE GOT THINGS TO DO.
-SANZO.
SANZO!
-"HEAVEN'S DOOR."
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
-JUST LOOK AT IT.
IT'S WHAT WE ALWAYS WANTED --
A PLACE WHERE
WE CAN TRULY BE FREE.
OUT HERE,
THERE IS NO HERESY OR TABOOS.
AND A LOVE AS PURE AS OURS
WOULD NEVER BE FORBIDDEN.
-YOU JUST CONTINUE BEING STRONG,
PRIEST GENJO SANZO.
[ FOOTSTEPS ECHOING ]
-WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME?
-THAT JACKASS
TOOK THE SEITEN SCRIPTURE
RIGHT OUT FROM UNDER MY NOSE.
I EXPECT TO GET IT BACK,
WITH INTEREST.
-THAT SCRIPTURE
BELONGS TO MY MASTER.
-MAYBE SO, BUT...
THIS HAS BECOME
A MATTER OF PRIDE.
-IT'S SO FITTING,
ISN'T IT, GOKU,
THAT THE OUTCASTS OF THIS WORLD
SHOULD BE THE FATHERS
OF THE NEXT?
BUT ISN'T THAT HOW IT SHOULD BE?
-WOW.
IT'S SO SHINY.
IT'S LIKE THE SUN.
[ GROWLS ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
SO, THIS IS YOUR TRUE NATURE.
-WHOA. WHAT IS IT?
-GET READY.
-WHAT?
-AAH!
-AAAAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
-YOU'VE BEEN A VERY BAD MONKEY.
-[ SHOUTS ]
-NOW YOU'VE DONE IT.
AGAIN.
HE'S SMILING AGAIN.
-STEP ASIDE.
-SANZO, WHAT ARE YOU --
-MONKEYS NEED TO BE TRAINED.
[ GUN CLATTERS ]
-DIDN'T I TELL YOU...
THAT I'D GET MY PRIDE BACK?
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE WE FOUGHT, EH, GOKU?
I GUESS YOU DON'T REMEMBER THAT.
WELL, THEN, SHALL WE START?
-A CREATURE LIKE YOU
IS NOT MEANT TO BE CHAINED.
YOU ARE TRULY ONE OF A KIND.
A SOUL LIKE YOURS
SHOULD BE FREE.
-[ GROWLS ]
-[ SHOUTING ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
[ MACHINE-GUN FIRE ]
-SCURRYING AROUND LIKE RATS.
-YOU'RE LOOKING A LITTLE WINDED.
YOU SHOULD REALLY CUT BACK
ON THOSE CIGARETTES.
-YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
-EXCELLENT STRATEGY.
I COMMEND YOU
ON YOUR TEAMWORK THUS FAR.
-STOP THIS.
PLEASE, SHIEN, YOU MUST SEE
THAT THIS IS POINTLESS.
-POINTLESS?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL WE WANT IS GOKU RETURNED
AND TO GET BACK
THE MATEN SCRIPTURE.
JUST HAND THEM OVER AND WE
CAN ALL STOP THIS FIGHTING.
IT'S SENSELESS.
-YOU SAID IT, DUDE!
BACK DOWN!
-I CAN'T DO THAT.
-WHY NOT?
-FIGHTING IS ALL WE KNOW.
FIGHTING IS OUR ONLY PURPOSE.
IT IS ONLY IN BATTLE
THAT WE KNOW WE ARE ALIVE.
ZENON AND I HAVE VOWED
TO SERVE HOMURA,
AND WE SHALL DO
WHATEVER HE ASKS OF US.
-[ GASPS ]
THAT MAKES NO SENSE.
-IT'S OKAY.
ONE THING I'VE LEARNED
IS YES-MEN NEVER LEARN
TO SAY NO TO ANYTHING.
-SO, SHALL WE DANCE?
-[ GASPS ]
SHIEN.
-UH?
-SHIEN...
-HOMURA, PLEASE GO ON AHEAD.
I WILL CATCH UP WITH YOU LATER.
I SHOULDN'T THINK THIS WILL TAKE
MORE THAN A FEW MOMENTS,
BUT PLEASE DON'T WAIT UP FOR ME.
I MAY WISH TO PROLONG
THE MOMENT.
-OF COURSE.
PLEASE TAKE YOUR TIME.
-HOW MANY CENTURIES HAS IT BEEN
SINCE I LET MY HAIR DOWN
AND TRULY FOUGHT IN EARNEST?
AND NOW I WILL TEACH YOU...
THE POWER OF GOD.
-[ GASPS ]
-GOD?
DON'T YOU KNOW?
GOD IS DEAD!
-[ SHOUTS ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
-[ GROWLS ]
-HE'S EVEN EVEN STRONGER
THAN BEFORE.
-AAH!
-HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
-AW, SHOOT.
-[ SHOUTING ]
-AAH!
-ARE YOU OKAY, YOU GUYS?
-WELL, THEN, IF I HAD KNOWN
YOU WERE THIS GOOD,
I WOULD'VE SAVED MY CHI.
-SO, YOU HAVE REGRETS.
-NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
BELIEVE ME,
I DON'T REGRET A SINGLE THING.
REGRETS ARE JUST A WAY
FOR THE FOOLISH AND THE GUILTY
TO PASS THE TIME.
-IS THAT SO?
-IT IS.
AND I AM.
I'M A FOOL --
A FOOL FOR ALWAYS DWELLING
ON A GUILT-RIDDEN PAST
THAT CAN NEVER BE CHANGED.
I WAS WEAK,
AND I CAN SEE THAT NOW.
-I WOULD HARDLY CALL YOU WEAK,
MY FRIEND.
-THAT'S VERY KIND OF YOU.
BUT TO BE ENTIRELY HONEST,
IF I HAVE ANY STRENGTH AT ALL,
IT'S ONLY BECAUSE
I HAVE A GROUP OF FRIENDS
THAT I NEED TO PROTECT.
-INTERESTING.
IT'S TOO BAD.
I WISH I HAD MORE TIME
TO DISCUSS THIS WITH YOU.
[ SCREAMS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
-I FEAR YOUR FRIENDS
WILL DIE SOON.
-DON'T WORRY.
THEY'RE NOT MY FRIENDS.
THOSE GUYS ARE ONLY MY SERVANTS.
THAT'S ALL.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
I-I'M NOT SURE HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN HOLD HIM BACK.
DO SOMETHING, GOJYO!
-SO WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO
ABOUT IT?
THIS DUDE'S HARD-CORE, MAN.
-GUYS, HELP ME!
THINK OF SOMETHING QUICK,
WILL YOU?!
-[ SCREECHES ]
-HAKURYUU.
-NO!
-THIS IS POINTLESS.
LAY OFF AND LET ME
HAVE A GO AT THEM.
-NO.
-I THINK I KNOW A WAY
TO SHATTER THIS QIGONG WAVE.
HAKURYUU, YOU TAKE IT FROM HERE!
-[ SQUEALS ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
-AH, AN ADMIRABLE EFFORT
BUT INADEQUATE, I'M AFRAID.
-OH?
THEN WHY DO YOU LOOK
SO CONCERNED?
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER,
I'D SAY YOU WERE BITTER.
THAT'S ABSURD.
-IS IT?
CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG,
BUT I'D SAY YOUR POWER
COMES AT A VERY HEAVY PRICE.
-NOTHING COMES
WITHOUT SACRIFICE, I'M AFRAID.
-BUT TO FORFEIT YOUR FEELINGS?
YOU CLOSED YOURSELF OFF
FOR SO LONG
THAT YOU CAN NO LONGER KNOW
JOY OR PAIN.
-THAT'S NOT TRUE.
-BUT WHAT'S IT ALL FOR?
IS IT JUST TO SERVE HOMURA?
I THINK
IT'S MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY
FROM SOMETHING --
SOMETHING YOU'RE AFRAID OF.
BUT WHAT?
-SHUT UP.
-WHAT ARE YOU RUNNING AWAY FROM?
IS IT SOMETHING
THAT YOU'VE DONE?
-SHUT UP!
-OR PERHAPS IT'S SOMETHING
YOU DIDN'T DO.
IS THAT IT?
-SHUT UP, SHUT UP,
SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
-NOW WHO'S THE ONE WITH REGRETS?
-[ GASPS ]
AAH!
-SHIEN!
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
-[ GROANING ]
YOU THINK...
THAT I AM A...COWARD?
-I'M SORRY.
I HAD NO RIGHT
TO PRY INTO YOUR PAST LIKE THAT.
I TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF YOUR WEAKNESS.
-I SEE,
AND I SHOULD'VE SEEN
YOUR ATTACK COMING.
I WOULD'VE DONE THE SAME THING.
YOU ARE RIGHT, MY FRIEND,
AND I AM A FOOL...
A FOOL WHO LIVES IN A PAST
THAT CAN'T BE CHANGED.
-SHIEN, NO!
-IT LOOKS LIKE I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO BREAK MY PROMISE.
-NO!
DON'T DO THIS, SHIEN!
-I'M AFRAID IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO MOVE ON.
-THEN MOVE ON TO THE NEW WORLD.
-I'M SORRY.
I MUST GO.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
IT WAS SUCH A BEAUTIFUL DREAM
WHILE IT LASTED.
AND, HAKKAI,
IT WAS AN HONOR
TO LOSE IN BATTLE
TO SUCH A WORTHY ADVERSARY.
[ RUMBLING ]
-[ SQUEALS ]
-HAKKAI!
-YOU JUST HAD TO PUSH IT.
-I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
-HMM?
-IT'S GONNA TAKE MORE THAN
A FEW MIND GAMES TO DEFEAT ME.
-ZENON.
-RELAX, MAN.
[ GROANING ]
-[ GROANING CONTINUES ]
-NOW YOU DIE.
-HEY, HOLD ON.
JUST WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE
HOW THIS LITTLE FARCE
OF YOURS PLAYS OUT?
-YOU CAN FILL ME IN LATER.
-YEAH, THAT'S REAL FUNNY.
WAIT TILL I GET AHOLD OF YOU.
HEY, MONKEY.
PLAYTIME'S OVER.
SO IF YOU'RE THROUGH WITH HIM,
LET'S GET STARTED.
-SORRY, GUYS, BUT I...
HAVE TO DO THIS.
[ MIKUNI SHIMOKAWA'S
"ALONE" PLAYS ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]