I'm starving.
When can we stop to eat?
Is that all you ever say,
you stupid monkey?!
And is that all you ever say?
Oh, dear god. Here we go again.
[Hakkai gasps in surprise]
What'd you do that for?
There are better ways to break
up the monotony, you know.
[Hakkai] I didn't have to.
[Gojyo & Goku] Huh?
[Gojyo] Come to think of it...
Cleaning up after demons
is one of our routines.
I don't think demons
could do all this.
[Goku] What a senseless
thing to do...
I know. Shouldn't there
be more corpses?
Yeah.
[Goku yells]
What now?
Is he alive?
Just barely.
Our... our caravan was
ambushed by demons.
[Goku] Huh?
You must... help me save them.
[Sanzo] Another distraction
I don't need.
[Goku] "The second son".
[Zenon] Surely a Founding
Scripture did not end up there.
[Shien] I would not put too
much stock in this rumor.
[Zenon] It's idle chatter
overheard from demons.
[Homura] How likely
is it, Shien?
I'd say it's about as likely
as winning the lottery.
But we coud take a look.
That bad, huh?
[Zenon] What the hell?
It's not like I've got
something better to do.
[Shien] Zenon?
[Zenon] You can't win
if you don't play, right?
If I hit the jackpot, I expect
you to throw me a big party.
[Shien] Honestly.
So this is it.
I'll be...
[Demons yelling and
villagers panicking]
[Demon laughs deviously]
[Demon 1] What the-?!
[Bald demon] Whoever did that
better come out right now!
Sorry, ladies. But I
can't have you torchin'
up the whole place, now can I?
[Bald demon yells]
[Demon yells]
Ah! A banishing rifle...
I'm outta here!
[Demons panic as
they try to leave]
[Demons yell]
Come on guys, that's no
way to greet visitors.
You could at least say "hello".
You get out of our way!
[Gojyo] We don't like
to move around too much.
[Goku] Yeah. Too much effort.
[Demons shout in frustration]
I give up!
[Demons panicking]
Hey! Come back here!
Hold up, Goku.
Hm?
Whattya know...
Why, you're Zenon.
So these guys are your minions?
[Dense demon] YAH!
[Dense demon yells]
Guess I spoke too soon.
[Zenon] You guys heard about
the Scripture too, eh?
[Gojyo] What?
[An old women yells]
[Goku] Huh?
[Old Lady] Oh Shunei!
Please don't hurt him!
Hand over your money.
And I'll take whatever
food you got layin' around.
Don't come any closer
or the kid gets it!
First you pillage,
then on to hostages.
You losers are all the same.
Should I take care of this?
[Zenon] I don't think
that's a wise idea.
Better leave this one to me.
Hmph.
What...? You arrogant...!
Why should YOU get to save him?
[Zenon] Because you'll just
get the hostage killed.
[Demon] I told you not
to come any closer!
Is that right?! Well
we'll just see about that!
[Demon shouts in surprise]
[Zenon] Get down, kid!
[Demon yells]
He's right. You would
have killed him with
a shot like that.
We planned it that way,
you moron!
[Zenon] Can you stand?
You bet!
[Owl hooting]
I'm afraid we don't
have much to offer,
but please make
yourselves at home.
Let's dig in!
So, what is one of Homura's
henchmen doing around
these parts?
It seemed like a nice place
to get some fresh air.
Really? Because I thought
you said something
about a Scripture.
I don't recall that.
Are you sure?
And what brings you here?
I didn't think the four of
you could bear to be outside
the presence of each
other's company.
You think we'd be together
if we didn't have to be?
[Gojyo] So, Sanzo and Hakkai
said they'd catch up as soon
as they dropped the
guy off at a doctor.
I expect they'll show up
sometime tomorrow if they
don't do any sightseeing.
So, you think demons
are responsible?
It's not really their style.
You didn't have anything to
do with this, did you?
Give me some credit now,
will ya?
Okay then, maybe Gyumaoh's
side is behind it.
So does that mean we should
put off our own showdown?
[Goku] More please!
Augh! You've ruined my
big, dramatic pause!
Hm?
It's right this way.
If there's anything at all
you need, just let me know.
Hey, you're that little kid that
was taken hostage, aren't you?
Thank you so much for saving me.
That mean ol' demon would
have killed me for sure.
[Zenon] My son would have
been about this age now.
What is it?
Hello? Is there
something you want?
Huh? Sorry... No thanks.
I'm fine.
[Zenon] Sheesh... When did
I become such a softy?
[Villagers talking and
giving instructions]
[Man 1] No, not that one!
[Man 1] This one!
[Man 2] Ack! You
dropped it on my foot.
[Man 3] Hey, tell him
to give me a hand!
[Villager] No, I can't say
that I have, but, ah,
can I interest you in some
calligraphy scrolls?
That's alright. So long.
[Zenon] I knew this
was a waste of time.
[Shunei shouts]
[Jerk kid 1] What's the
matter, Shunei? You fall?
You should watch
where you're going!
Yeah, then maybe we wouldn't
knock you down so much!
[Zenon] What a mess.
[Zenon] You sure must like
getting pushed around like that.
[Shunei] What makes
you say that?
Because you don't do
anything about it.
I don't see any point.
I could never beat up those
bunch of jerks anyway.
Then you've lost
before you started.
If I were your father,
I'd beat you up for not
standing up to those kids.
Well, so you live at that
inn with your grandparents,
is that right?
[Shunei] Mmhmm.
[Zenon] What happened
to your parents?
I'm an orphan.
Demons killed them.
They're both gone, because
those damn demons keep coming.
Each time they come and each
time more people are killed.
Sorry, I didn't know.
[Mirei screams]
[Zenon gasps]
[Zenon] Mirei!
You bastard!
[Souei] Here's your
lovely wife back.
A fighter to the very end.
It's her fault for
not listening to me!
You will pay for
what you have done!
You would never kill me,
would you?
Gods are forbidden
to take a life.
[Zenon] Bastard!
[Zenon] An illusion?!
[Souei chuckles]
[Souei] Kind of hard to
catch me when I'm not
even here, isn't it?
I wish you the best, Zenon.
Farewell.
[Zenon] Now... come at me.
Don't hold back. You just try to
imagine that I'm the demon who
killed your parents.
[Shunei gives a battlecry]
Come on now, try harder.
You won't stop those
bullies with that swing.
[Wood clanking
against metal loudly]
Who the hell would be making
a racket this early?
It's noon already, moron.
[Goku] You mean...
I missed breakfast?!
I wouldn't of guessed
he liked kids.
[Goku] Huh?
[Gojyo] Nothing,
let's get lunch!
[Goku] Yeah!
[Shunei breathes heavily]
You're starting to
get the hang of it.
It won't be too long before
you're takin' on demons.
Hm!
There's not much of
a village left.
You might have to move some
place else pretty soon, kid.
We can't leave this place.
I once overheard
my dad say that.
He said there's something
in the village that we
have to protect.
[Zenon] Huh?
[Shunei] It's a magical
treasure that must be kept
from falling into
the wrong hands.
My dad showed it to me
once before he died.
So this magic treasure...
wouldn't happen to be a
certain scroll, would it?
[Shunei] Uh, yeah.
How did you know?
I believe I just
hit the jackpot.
[Goku] Can I have some more?
Oh, of course you can!
Don't be such a pig, you pig.
[Goku] I can't help it
I didn't have breakfast!
You're one to talk, drinking all
their wine in the middle of the
afternoon, you big lush.
Hey, I have to make up for
lost time before those
two prudes get here.
Get off my back.
[Hakkai] We came all this way
and still couldn't save him.
[Sanzo] People die
when they die.
There's no point in trying
to make sense out of it.
Master Sanzo, I'm sorry
you couldn't save him.
But I found someone with
information that might
save others.
If large number of people are
being kidnapped at one time,
then it sounds like
the work of Ikaku.
Ikaku?
He is a demon that
feasts on human souls.
But once their spirits
have been devoured,
he keeps the human bodies alive
to use for his amusement.
And where is this Ikaku now?
[Man] I've heard rumors that
he's using the village of Koton
as his base of operations.
[Mayor] Is something wrong?
It's just that... that's
where we're supposed to
meet up with our friends.
That's the place.
I'll find it in there, huh?
[Zenon] Listen Shunei...
[Shunei] Yes?
You know, years ago I
lost my family to a demon.
A wife and a son.
He'd be about your age
if he hadn't been killed.
[Mirei screams]
[Souei chuckles]
[Zenon] My god! Mirei!
I could not save her.
Don't ever let them
kill you, Shunei.
If you let them, a lot
of people will be hurt.
[Zenon] Is it in here?
[Shunei] Yes...
Well then...
By the way, kid.
Uh, yeah?
It's alright. I won't hate you
if you lied to me about the
scripture being here.
[Gojyo] Zenon, wait!
It's a trap!
[Shunei gasps]
The old lady at the inn
finally fessed up when
we questioned them!
All these people were kidnapped.
They're being held against their
will by a demon named Ikaku.
It's all just an elaborate
trap to ensnare you.
Even this kid!
You keep your hands off!
What happened?!
You've gotta help Zenon!
You just gotta help him!
But you just...
I didn't want him to die!
[Ikaku] I doubt even a god could
have survived getting crushed
and skewered like that.
[Goku] Who's talking?!
[Gojyo] Is that Ikaku?!
[Ikaku] I was only ordered to
take care of Homura's henchman,
but since you're here,
I might as well rack
up some brownie points.
[Loud crashing sound]
[Shunei] What about Zenon?!
[Gojyo] We hafta get outta here!
[Shunei] Zenon!
[Ikaku] Hold it right there!
[Demons growling]
Let me guess...
Ikaku, am I right?
[Ikaku] You'll be put to rest,
just like that friend of yours!
But I'm not sleepy yet!
Prepare for their destruction!
[Mom] No!
Please, please I beg you!
Don't attack while
my son is down there!
But you promised you wouldn't
hurt our little boy if we did
everything you told us to do!
[Shunei] Mom! Dad!
[Mom & Dad] Shunei!
[Gojyo] So the little tyke's
not an orphan either.
I'm afraid these two boys
are not to be trifled with.
We're going to need
every advantage we
have to defeat them.
Just hope that luck
will be on your side.
[Both] Please no!
Fire away!
[Demon yells]
[Demon 2 yells]
Why that was...
A machinegun!
Impossible!
[Shunei] Zenon!
I'm sorry! Forgive me!
[Zenon] I knew.
Those tears I saw you shed...
They were not the tears
of someone who had lost
their loved ones.
They were the tears of someone
who was about to lose them.
Fire! Mow them all down!
[Goku] Missed me!
[Gojyo] Here we go!
Stick close to me, you got it?
Yeah...
[Demon yells]
[Zenon] You catch on quick, kid.
You were right!
That move really works!
Stop goofing around!
I told you to kill
these guys already!
Would you shut him up?!
Would I?!
Wait! Don't kill him, Goku!
How dare you mess
with people's hearts?
[Ikaku yells]
[Dad grunts, mom yells in pain]
[Shunei grunts in pain]
[Zenon] Shunei!
[Gojyo] What is this?
The dirty bastard carried around
their souls in his stomach.
When you killed Ikaku...
You killed all of the
townspeople he had devoured
and kept inside him.
We can't save them now.
It can't be... Speak to me!
Shunei! Open your eyes, Shunei!
I told you not to die, didn't I?
[Shunei] This is what I get
for lying to you, Zenon.
When I go to the world beyond,
I wonder if I'll meet
your son there...
I can't wait to meet him...
I know that we'll be friends...
[Zenon] No, not again. Shunei...
[Zenon screams in frustration]
[Zenon] Shunei... Say hi
to my son for me, will ya?
I know the two of
you will get along...
Just like you got
along with me.