This is really pathetic.
[Hakuryu whines]
[Door opens]
Hey, hey, hey! Who's the man?
Check out the catch I got,
you guys!
[Goku] Oooh! We're gonna
eat tonight, fellas!
[Gojyo] Dumbass...
[Goku] One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Nine, ten...
Eleven!
There, that makes two each.
But wait a minute. That still
leaves me with one extra.
I think I should get that
one since I caught them all.
That's fair. Yeah,
that's totally fair.
Move over, Hakuryu, I need some
salt. Salt... there it is!
[Goku] I could get
some if you stopped-
[Hakuryu squeaks]
What the hell do you mean...
you get the extra one?!
[Gojyo] We always
settle our disputes with
rock-paper-scissor, remember?
[Hakkai] My, my.
[Hakkai] You do have some
tasty looking trout here.
[Goku] It's okay.
I'll eat it, really.
Hey! You're taking
the biggest one!
[Gojyo] That's only fair
if you get the extra one.
[Goku] I caught them!
So I get to decide who
gets what! Now hand it over!
[Gojyo] That's only because
we let you catch them!
Hakkai! Are you trying
to cut ahead of us?!
[Goku] "Fighting the system."
Having trouble sleeping?
Will Sanzo... be alright?
I'm sure he'll pull through.
[Goku] Konzen!
Where are you going?
Tenpy's place is this way!
Come on! I'll show
you a short cut!
Tenpy's...? Why you...
[Goku] Hurry, hurry!
[Konzen] Damn.
[Goku] Hurry! Hurry!
[Goddess] Hmph. Take a
look at this, Jiroushin.
[Goddess] Now that's something
you don't see everyday.
[Goku] See? I told you
this way was quicker!
[Jiroushin] Well, whaddya know?
[Goddess] Did you ever...
[Goku] Hey, keep up! I know lots
[Goddess] think you'd see
someone leading HIM by the hand?
[Goku] of ways to get around!
C'mon, I'll show you!
[Jiroushin] Well, I'll be...
[Goku] I can't wait.
[Goku] Oh, I can't
wait to get there!
[Goddess] That little
runt is something else.
Tenpy, hey! Where should
I put these things?
Oh those? Just put them on
the back bookshelf somewhere.
It sure is great to have someone
with your strength around, Goku.
[Konzen] Gadnabbit.
I only came here because
Goku badgered me into it.
I don't see why I should clean
your room for you, you lazy,
manipulative bastard.
[Tenpou laughs]
But it suits you so well.
Hey. Why isn't Ken here?
Where is he?
He had to report to the
main palace for a military
roll call, I'm afraid.
And you didn't?
[Tenpou] The order was issued
to Prince Nataku's army,
fortunately.
Well, that's strange. Isn't
Nataku still recovering?
Yes, but I'm sure
the administration doesn't
care at all about that tidbit.
He's just their puppet,
after all.
Awesome! Can I borrow this?!
Can I?! Can I, please?!
Of course you can.
[Goku] Woo-hoo!
I'll be, so the chimp
can read, can he?
I love this one! It's about the
crime fighting meat bun of doom
and his band of friends:
Pizza Pocket, Curry Curtis and
the sweet Madam Bean-Jam.
Isn't it delicious?!
Sorry I asked.
[Tenpou chuckles]
It didn't take him long
to master the fundamentals
of reading and writing,
that's good.
He picks things up pretty
quickly if it's something
he's interested in.
Tell me, how well-stocked
is your library?
Oooh, I keep a little bit
of everything, to be
honest with you.
Tell you what, why don't
you lend me one of your
favorite titles sometime?
I just might do that.
[Nataku] I can show you all the
short cuts and hiding places.
I know one spot where you
can stuff yourself with
raspberries until you puke.
Come on, I'll show you!
[Goku laughing]
[Maiden] Lord Nataku...
Time to get up. Your
father is waiting for you.
[Crowd chatting]
Not another campaign.
This is a perpetual war.
[Soldier] What's the point of
having a War Prince around
if you don't use him?
All we have to do is sit back
and watch the fireworks.
Attention!
Prince Nataku, come forward.
Your Emperor requires
your service.
I need you in the field.
Yes.
[Kenren] Excuse me,
your highness.
[Official] Who speaks?!
[Kenren] Humble subordinate
to the Dragon of
the Western Seas,
General Kenren, Sire.
General! What is the reason
for your disruption?
Forgiveness, sire, but I
could not help but notice
that Nataku's wounds are
not yet fully healed.
So in honor of the courage
Nataku showed serving
the Emperor...
I humbly request that you please
allow my army to fight in
Prince Nataku's place.
[The crowd murmurs]
Be quiet. Surely you
do not honestly believe
that your army can
replace Prince Nataku.
I'd like to think we'd
do better than all these
coddled infants who don't like
to get their hands dirty.
What are you implying,
General Kenren?!
You're way outta line, General!
General Kenren, I won't
let you disparage my son.
NOT in this manner.
He is the best warrior
in the Heavens, bar none.
And his patriotism
is beyond reproach.
If he is called to serve,
he will take the field
as duty dictates.
Son... am I right?
[Nataku] Yes, father.
You make me proud, Nataku.
[Nataku, softly] Thank you.
As you know, General...
defying the emperor
is a sacrilege.
You're confined to quarters.
Aaaw! I'm still not
allowed to see Nataku?
I haven't been able to talk
to him since he got back!
He must be hurt really bad.
I know, and I don't like turning
you away every day, either.
That's okay. After all, it's
not your fault he's been hurt.
Take this! Give it to Nataku
for me. Will you do that?
Of course. I can do that.
"Confined to quarters", my ass!
Feels more like toture and
imprisonment if you ask me!
You should have
consulted with me.
I would have passed on
your concerns to the
good Emperor myself.
It was more fun this way,
you have to agree.
Looks to me like
you had a blast.
Oh please, this was nothing.
Nataku's playful little
nudge hurt more than this.
If you wanna know what
tortures me, man...
it's seeing the way this
place treats that kid.
But even that can't compare
to the pain of knowing...
the brat can't even
admit it hurts.
[Jiroushin] Merciful Goddess...
About this document...
[Jiroushin gasps]
What the-?!
Don't you love it?
I wouldn't have thought...
Uh, did you make it?
You've got to be kidding me.
I just picked it up.
[Jiroushin] Picked it up?
That's right.
[Goku] What?! Nataku's
still not better?
[Maiden] Yes, I'm afraid you
won't be able to see him again.
[Goddess] Flowers, disregarded
and forgotten.
Like the one they
were intended for.
[Kenren] Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
That hurt, you
stupid little runt!
Don't you listen to him, Goku.
You just make it as
tight as you can,
so it won't come loose, okay?
What have you got against me,
mullet head?
Hm. I don't even
know where to begin.
The way you embarrassed
the Jade Emperor.
[Kenren] Huh?
[Tenpou] You got yourself
thrown into prison,
and interrogated as a suspected
insurgent, and you're still
cracking jokes about it.
I feel sorry for whoever has
to follow your orders.
Please tell me, what did I
do to deserve this suffering?
Yeah, yeah, I can't help myself.
It's in my nature.
Oh, I know it is.
But it was idiotic of you to
make Li Touten your enemy.
He has had you dismissed
from your military duties.
So?
[Tenpou] Don't you "so" me.
I'm sorry, but things don't
roll off my back as easily
as they do yours.
I'll have you know this
makes it difficult for me.
I can't work for anyone.
[Door opens]
[Kenren] Hey, now!
I'm going out for a little walk.
I've done all I can to
patch things up here.
Goku, keep him out
of trouble, will ya?
[Goku] Have a good time!
Hey! What if I have
to take a wizz?!
[Tenpou] I'll mop up after
you when I get back.
Hey, Goku, would you mind
going after Tenpou for me?
I'm on watch duty.
Listen to me!
He may not look it, but Tenpou
can be more impulsive than I am.
[Goku] What's "impulsive" mean?
[Kenren] It means...
[Door opens]
[Kenren] you don't want
to see him lose his temper.
[Touten] Field Marshal Tenpou.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
[Tenpou] I don't have
much patience for
pleasantries right now,
so let's get right to
the point, shall we?
I demand you reinstate
General Kenren at once.
I thought you would come.
Please, have a seat.
Now, I don't want to
appear rude here,
but since when have you been in
a position to offer me a seat?
As I recall, you have
no affiliation with the
Heavenly Army whatsoever.
Unless I'm mistaken, that gives
you no authority to meddle in
military affairs at all.
[Touten chuckles] The Jade
Emperor has seen fit to
entrust all military
matters to me.
I speak with the
emperor's authority.
You have absolutely no shame.
To sacrifice your own son,
Nataku, for the purpose of
advancing your own career?
You make me sick.
[Touten] You have
a pretty face.
I'm sure there are lots
of other jobs for you,
and your red haired boyfriend,
to pursue.
Ya think?
My lord, are you alright?!
You bastard! Seize him!
[Tenpou gives a small shout]
[Touten] This is too precious.
What a sight.
Now do you see? They no longer
follow orders from you.
And they never will again.
I am in charge.
You know what?
I think this calls
for an interrogation.
Don't you...
pick on him!
Who the hell is this brat?!
Goku?! Wha-why are you...
General Kenren told me
to come and get you.
He said you'd probably
be in big trouble.
[Tenpou] Hmph. Did he now?
What in the...
Don't you dare lay
a hand on Tenpy.
Do you understand me?
Come on, Tenpy. Let's rock.
Yeah, let's... rock.
[Door opens and closes]
Should we just let 'em
walk away, my lord?
Stand down. It won't
change anything.
[Konzen] Tell me, are you and
Kenren sharing the same stylist?
Yes, and I think the fashion is
bound to catch on, eventually.
Don't I look more rugged?
You're full of it.
You better not have
gotten into trouble again.
[Konzen] Goku.
[Goku] Huh?
Let me see... I can't
remember, it's a secret.
[Kenren whistles]
[Konzen sighs] Oh, whatever.
Just don't drag Goku into
anything too weird.
He's already hated enough
around here as it is.
Well, I assume you're not here
to show off your bruised faces.
Now what is it?
They've called for another
military intervention.
They're gonna send Nataku
back to the Lower World.
Let's all welcome him home.
Ah! I'll go!
[Kenren] You coming?
[Konzen] No, I'm afraid
[Konzen] I have to deliver
this document to the old hag.
[Goku] Let's go, let's go!
[Kenren] Hold on.
[Goku] I finally
get to see Nataku!
[Konzen] Tenpou...
I know, Konzen. Goku shouldn't
get too attached to Nataku.
That's what's bothering
you, right?
Li Touten's son may very
well become a casualty of
his unquenchable
thirst for power.
Yet none of us can seem to help
wanting to see it, for just
a little while longer.
That innocent smile...
[Konzen] You can't be serious.
Kenren is no longer the general?
They kept their jobs, but not
without some heavy duty lobbying
from your friend, Tenpou.
But Li Touten is vindictive.
It will come at a heavy price.
Then what about their injuries?
[Goddess] Injuries?
[Konzen] They never told
me about any of this.
[Goddess] Hmph. I'm sure they
didn't think it was worth
bothering you about.
[Konzen] Why am I always the
last to know what's going on
inside the administration?
It makes me sick!
Oh, please.
How long have you
been here anyway?
You would think you'd figure out
that you only know what you
find out for yourself.
[Crowds cheering loudly]
[Goku] Nataku! Nataku!
Over here!
I'm really glad you're back!
It's you!
Nataku?! Nataku!
It's me! Don't you remember?!
I'm your friend!
What's wrong with you?!
Can't you see me?!
Nataku!
[Goddess] I wonder...
Will you still be his sun?
[Goku] Sanzo?
What's the matter?
Did you have a nightmare
or something?
What's with me?
It's so weird.
I don't cry.
What's all the tears for?
I... caught us some fish.
Huh?
Real nice ones.
I wanted to share
them with everyone,
but you... but you wouldn't
wake up, so I guess I just...
I just... wanted...
to eat them together.
And I...!
It's just dinner, man.
You're such an idiot.
I know.
[Sanzo] Let's go!
Yeah!