Looks like he's arrived.
[Homura] Remove his shackles.
But... but you can't be serious.
[Homura] Just do it.
[Both] Aye.
I'm not quite sure if I
should thank you or not.
Please don't. There's
no need for that.
Then I apologize.
Because although I am grateful,
I'm afraid I'm going to
have to kill you and your
charming little companions.
[Undertaker] Why
are you laughing?
Why do you think we're
laughing, you moron?
We're all laughing
because you're a joke.
Oh, I'll show you funny.
Well he does seem to
have spirit, Zenon.
I tell you what.
I'll make you a deal. If you
can touch us, we'll let you go.
Okay, but be forewarned.
I don't intend to
spare any of you.
I won't show any mercy
once you're dead.
[Shien] You shall now be reborn
as a holy demon in our service.
Confer divinity.
So it is done.
You have but one command.
To obtain the Maten Scripture
priest Genjo Sanzo wears.
Go.
Yes. Your wish is my command.
You really think he
can pull it off?
He's been strengthened,
but that's no guarantee.
We shall see.
It seems like a decent
place to start.
Isn't that right, Son Goku?
[Goku] "An Invitation to Hell."
[Gojyo] I'm exhausted.
I can't even muster enough
energy to punch Goku.
[Goku] That would piss me off
if I weren't so damn hungry.
Hold tight. We'll be
in town soon enough.
So just be a little
patient, okay?
[Gojyo & Goku] Alright.
[Sanzo] You guys wear me out.
[Gojyo] I don't know, this
town's a little too quiet.
I don't understand,
where are all the people?
Maybe everybody's
just on vacation.
Yeah, right!
That hurt! I was serious!
I know you were.
Something here is wrong.
I think you're right, Sanzo.
I don't even see any
animals around here.
Look there! See?
Got a problem with wells, dude?
There's no water, Goku.
Don't you see? Even the
ditches have all dried up.
And not a single plant to
be found anywhere. Nothing.
At the very least, you
ought to see a weed.
Must be a ghost town.
[Sanzo] Wrong.
The buildings look as
if they're brand new.
They're all on vacation.
[Gojyo] Is this a joke?
[Hakkai] They look like coffins.
I don't like this.
[Undertaker] Welcome
to my little utopia.
Do you like them?
I made them especially for
you four fine gentlemen.
I do hope I got the sizes right.
Why you-!
Where are the townspeople?
Washed away.
"Washed away?"
They made such a
clutter, you see.
So I thought I'd just tidy
up the place a little bit.
What's his deal? Weirdo.
Oh, who knows?
Hey, maybe the heat's
fried his brain, ya think?
[Undertaker] I'm afraid your
bravado will not save you.
Why?
Because it is your fate
to die by my hand.
Afraid not!
If you will allow me...
to introduce myself.
I am the Undertaker.
That's what my friends call me.
But you can call
me what you like.
You'll still end up
in these coffins.
Until then, enjoy your stay.
So, what do we do?
Mr. Six-Feet-Under does seem
pretty intent on killing us.
[Sanzo] I won't let
him ruin my pool game.
Besides, he knows
where to find us.
No doubt about that.
What do you think happened
to all those villagers?
That's the one question
I'd like answered.
[Goku] He killed them.
I can smell their blood.
Now what kind of bar
doesn't serve any alcohol?
Not very hospitable, is it?
[Goku] Why isn't there any food?
Not even on the ground! Man...
Found some!
There's no way.
Yum! Here I come!
[Undertaker] You'll be a simple
one to catch, won't you?
Your appetites make it
so easy to ensnare you.
That little... The next time
I see him, I'm gonna...!
I won't stop looking
until I find some food!
Oh, you will, huh? What's new?
So are we having fun yet?
You bet. This is
the time of my life.
Is that right? So
glad to hear it.
So tell me, do you kill people
by annoying them to death?
You stupid retard!
I told you, I like
to keep things tidy.
So I rid of anything that marred
this town's perfect beauty.
But don't fret. You and
your friends will all be
joining them soon enough.
That so?
[Undertaker] Don't
even think about it!
Ah, that was my last pack!
Oh relax, pinky.
You know it's your
health I'm worried about.
You should thank me.
Listen.
Four people before you
asked me to quit smoking.
Do you wanna know
what happened to them?
No.
I killed every last one.
That's enough. I told you
once before, I like to
keep things tidy.
Don't push it.
[Gojyo] You crossed the line.
[Sanzo] What do you think?
[Hakkai] I haven't really
formed an opinion yet.
It's one thing to try to use
your lightning quick wit, but...
You don't like his
theatrics, do you?
That's right.
Sanzo, look!
Looks like the funeral
preparations are underway.
This guy annoys me.
[Undertaker] What's the matter?
Doesn't my captive audience
like my little performance?
He's back.
We're on schedule.
Come morning, your funeral
will start as planned.
Sorry, but I was never
very big on these kinds
of formal affairs.
Never was one to keep
schedules either.
[Undertaker] Ah-ah-ah!
Not so fast.
[Hakkai] Hakuryu!
[Undertaker] You let
your guard down.
[Hakkai] Are you all right?!
[Hakuryu squeaks pitifully]
[Hakkai] Hakuryu!
Are you all right?
Hakuryu!
I'm was so...
stupid for not seeing that move.
Thank God. At least
it's not serious.
But to attack a poor,
defenseless creature
like that... man.
I know.
So they don't have water,
or people, but how can
a town have no food?!
There are no cigarettes,
no liquor, and no women.
Augh! That's it! I
say we blow this town!
Don't wanna.
Why not?!
You've got to be joking, man.
You want us to take off after
the way he mocked us?
Right, monk?
Huh. You got that right.
Besides, he's no moron.
I'm sure he's taken care
of that contingency already.
At the very least, I bet he
put up a wall or something
to keep us here in this town.
It's such an eerie
feeling though.
How he actually seems to
anticipate our every move.
That's not hard with these two.
[Gojyo & Goku] What did
you say?!
They're so unbelievably
predictable.
But the show is far from over.
The curtain has just
raised on my little play.
Hey, Sanzo.
Lend me a smoke, will ya?
No way.
Don't be such a Scrooge!
I've gotta have my fix, man!
If memory serves me correctly,
I seem to recall someone saying
my smokes tasted like shit.
I need nicotine right
now! Cough 'em up!
Let go of me. That is,
if you want to live,
you red-haired fairy.
I NEED NICOTINE!
Okay, I think it's time to
give it a rest, you guys.
This is exactly what
he wants us to do.
You bastard!
You son of a...
Hey, you guys. I think
I may be hallucinating.
I see a plate of meatbuns
right there in front of me.
You're not nuts. We all
see it there too, Goku.
Hey! So it is real!
Oh, I didn't say that.
Look around.
[Goku] What is this?
[Gojyo] It's just another
one of his magic tricks.
A rather elaborate one at that.
[Goku] Hmm.
Alright! Look alive, barkeep!
Just serve me anything,
so long as I can eat it!
It's not real, stupid monkey!
It's you!
[Sanzo] Don't, they're
an illusion too.
[Goku] Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Hm. That's quite a show.
It is, but I don't care much
for his ubject matter.
That's way too gory for me.
Ah-huh. I don't know
about you gentlemen,
but I say we close the curtains
on this three-penny opera.
But how do we do that?
That's my job.
Mr. Six-Feet-Under's
not the only one who can
play games around here.
[Goku] "With My Compliments".
The tables turn.
Wait till that neat
freak gets a load of
this little embellishment.
[Hakkai hums as he
defaces property]
Hey, Sanzo. Tell me, do you
think he'll really come?
Oh yeah. This is his
town, after all.
[Undertaker] Stop it!
[Sanzo] Told you.
[Goku] That was quick.
Stop it! You've
ruined my village!
Ruined it! You ruined it!
[Sanzo] Why don't you come
down here and make us stop?!
Yeah, and you better hurry.
There won't be much of
your village left.
Just stop it. This is my
village. This is my utopia.
Alright then.
If that's the way you little
boys want it, I'll clean house.
I think he heard.
This time for real, I hope.
No need to worry. It's
really me this time.
I sure hope those coffins
come in your size!
[Undertaker] You couldn't
kill me, little one.
I say it's time we show this
guy who he picked a fight with.
He's going to regret
this, I guarantee it.
You're going to be the
ones who'll be sorry.
You could have had the
chance to at least live
until the morning.
[Goku] We'll live
longer than that!
Looks like you're pretty good
at hopping around, little bunny.
Dodge this!
[Undertaker] You're
so thick headed.
Who're you calling thick
headed, you jerk?!
[Undertaker] Why you, of course.
[Gojyo cries out in pain]
Bastard!
Don't bother. You can't hit me.
I'm much too fast for
you and your friends.
I know every move you're going
to make before you even make it.
And I know what you're thinking-
I've had about enough of
your self-promotional crap.
Taking advantage of a bunch
of traveling morons is
nothing to brag about.
[Undertaker] You tore my jacket.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you!
I'll kill you!
[Sanzo] Nice job.
[Hakkai] Thanks.
These stupid coffins are
beginning to annoy me.
[Sanzo] He can use them as
either shields or weapons.
Rather troublesome.
Which means we should...
Here goes!
[Sanzo] There's my opening!
I told you I knew what
you were thinking before
you even thought it.
Goku, Gojyo, can either of
you destroy those coffins?!
[Gojyo] Right, he'll have
nothing to protect him then.
[Goku] Then let's
get to it, Gojyo!
Good luck. They won't
break that easily.
[Undertaker gasp]
It's my turn.
[Undertaker] Impossible!
Time for a little
spring cleaning.
No, don't! Stay back!
Keep away from me!
And this one is for...
not having any food, jackass!
And this one...
is for your no smoking policy.
[Hakkai] It's okay. I'm
not holding a grudge.
[Sanzo] Looks like I'm next.
Maten Scripture, I call upon
you to use your power to
cast my enemy back into...
OBLIVION!
[Undertaker] HOMURA!
[Sanzo] You messed
with the wrong guys.
What did he say?!
Homura! He said Homura!
Is it still bothering
you, Sanzo?
A little.
Man, talk about a shithole.
I thought I was going to go
crazy in that stupid dump.
Same here. That place
was pure hell, man.
It was a dry county, and no
smoking section to be found.
Maybe that's exactly
what Heaven's like.
No way! Then I'd rather
have a table downstairs.
[Sanzo] Too late.
I know exactly where
we're all going.
So, it's Hell after
all then, eh?
Nope.
West!