[Goku] This sucks.
[Gojyo] When did you become
such a slow poke, Hakkai?
[Hakkai] I'm sorry, but
this is as fast as I can
go on this narrow road.
Come on. Step on it, will ya?
I'm about to go
insane over here.
I guess you wouldn't be
so bored if I decided
to drive off that cliff.
Tch.
[Goku] When are we gonna eat?
[Sanzo] Shut up.
Come on! Show a little
pity! My poor stomach's
all tied up in knots!
[Sanzo] Well, I could always
unravel some of those knots
for you, if you like.
[Goku's stomach growls loudly]
No need for that!
[Sanzo] If you're so hungry,
eat the grass on the side
of the road or something.
What?! Where is it?!
I don't see any grass!
[Loud rumbling]
[Goku] "The Arrogance
of the Gods."
[Jiroushin] Merciful Goddess!
Merciful Goddess!
Souto... Souto has taken
his subordinates and-
[Goddess] Relax, I know.
It looks to me like
Homura's not the only
one bored with this place.
How can you sit there?
If you knew that Homura
was going to do this,
shouldn't you at least
be trying to bring him
back to the heavens?
Why waste my time? You
know what he's like when
he's all wound up like that.
Besides, Souto's little band
of mercenaries has already
joined forces with Homura.
But Merciful Goddess, you know
what Souto's soldiers can do!
They were able to easily
defeat a force ten times their
size in the last mock battle.
Believe me, you do not want
these men as your enemy.
But as talented as they are,
they're still just common
soldiers lead by an
incompetent general.
Lesser men have tried, and
greater men have failed.
But, Merciful Goddess...
Besides, who can blame him?
Seeing how he's been
treated up here.
I suspect many more will seek
to serve Homura in the future.
[Jiroushin] You
can't be serious!
[Goddess] Still, I didn't really
think he was such a fool.
Souto's boys, eh?
I have heard the stories.
Your highness, I am sure
we can complete any
mission you ask of us.
Please, my lord. Let us
serve your high purpose.
We're yours.
[All] Yes, Sir!
[Shien] Homura...
Tell me, have you ever
heard of the Sanzo party?
[Souto] Yes.
I want you to destroy them,
and bring to me
the Maten Scripture.
If you do that,
I'll consider it.
[All] Aye!
I promise, we will not fail you.
So what is their status?
Aye.
Commander, I've spotted
some clothing.
They appear to be
Goku's and Gojyo's.
[Souto] I see.
Never the less, we still
don't know if we got them all.
Some still might have escaped.
But even if they did
manage to get away,
I seriously doubt
they'll survive the
traps we set for them.
They will die... for our future!
Commander, I've found
two sets of footprints.
Two of them must have escaped.
[Souto] Jikoku!
Yeah.
[Souto] Ryokusho!
Yes, Sir!
[Souto] Sekieki!
Aye!
[Souto] Go!
[All] Yes, Sir!
[Hakkai] First a boulder
lands on us, and now this.
Just a little
coincidence, right?
Sure it is.
It's all the work of some
out of control fur trapper.
[Hakkai] Somehow I don't
believe that's the case.
What do you think? You
think those two made it?
I'm afraid we can't get rid of
dear Gojyo and pain in my ass
monkey boy that easily.
35, 36, 37...
That's it. They're
in the minefield.
How can he be so stupid?!
The fool has allowed us to
pinpoint his exact location.
It won't be long before Jikoku
and the others find them.
[Outo] Shall I take a look?
Leave them. For now.
The Scripture is
our first priority.
[Souto] You can't hide from
Jikoku forever, Genjo Sanzo.
[Hakkai] Sanzo?
[Sanzo] Yeah, I know.
[Sekieki] Impressive.
They've evaded every
single one of our traps.
Heh, I gotta be honest here. It
wouldn't be any fun if we could
get rid of them that easily.
Now would it, gentlemen?
Let's all remember why
we're here, gentlemen.
This is no joy ride.
We're after that
sacred scripture.
[Jikoku] Sekieki!
[Sekieki] Yeah?
Listen here. Do try
to restrain yourself.
The Maten Scripture's no
good to any of us burned up.
[Sekieki] Hmph.
Here goes.
Sure looks that way.
That was close!
Now where the hell do
you think you're going?
Say your prayers, demon!
A god?!
You got that right!
And you should be praying to us!
[Sanzo] "Us" huh? So
he's not working alone.
That man bore a chakra on his
forehead, the sign of a god.
Just my luck.
[Outo] Commander, the
team has made contact and
engaged the Sanzo party.
Well done. He used a smoke
screen to confuse them,
then he split them up
and attacked each of
them individually.
It was truly a textbook
maneuver, my friend.
[Hakkai] Sanzo?
Sanzo?
[Ryokusho] Too slow!
How sad to have traveled
all this way just to die.
Ow! [pained groaning]
[Ryokusho] I usually kill people
much more gracefully than this,
but we're in kind of a hurry,
so this will have to do.
Now die!
It's not so subtle, but it
certainly gets the job done!
Commander, it looks
like Ryokusho took
care of Cho Hakkai.
He's gone to regroup
with the others.
I see.
So that leaves just one.
Genjo Sanzo!
A spry one.
Sekieki, don't just stand
there, do something, will ya?!
Ha! Thought you'd never ask.
Damn Sekieki. I
told him no bombs.
Commander, with all those
explosions, won't he be making
the others vulnerable
to friendly fire?
You're right. I'll
go reign him in.
Outo, you continue your
surveillance, just to be safe.
Right.
Sekieki, hold back!
Scripture's no good to us
if you burn the damn thing!
Looks like you need all
the help you can get.
Don't blame me if
things get out of hand.
[Sanzo] Good. They're
fighting amongst themselves.
[Jikoku] Got him!
[Sekieki] You aren't
getting away from me!
[Jikoku] Commander!
[Souto laughs]
[Souto] Having a hard time?
Sanzo has earned his reputation.
But the legend dies right here.
He can't evade us forever.
[All] Yes, Sir!
Damn, out of fuel.
This sucks.
Whaddya know, if it
isn't another one.
I thought they taught you monks
a respect for mother nature,
or did you skip holy
class that day?
You know, that's funny.
All this time I thought
tobacco was a part of nature.
Keep blowin' smoke.
You're gonna burn.
Just you try it. You
won't get away with it
this time, Priest Sanzo.
[Souto and company laugh]
Hehe, well it looks like
we finally got him.
Let's see...
Oh shit!
There's no point in fighting.
Hand over the Maten
Scripture and we'll go.
I don't think so.
Do you really want to join
your friends so badly?
My friends, huh?
I don't think I've ever
thought of any of those
guys as my friends.
What the hell are
we waiting for?
Let's kill the bastard already!
Quiet!
You know, I could put in a
good word with Homura for you,
and he just might spare
your miserable life.
I have no intention of spending
the rest of my life as his
little hunting
dog like you guys.
Shut up! Don't be such a smart
ass! It'll get you killed!
I'm not not so sure.
I'm still here, aren't I?
We can take care of
that soon enough!
I believe you mentioned
my friends earlier.
You wouldn't happen to know
where they might be hiding,
would you?
Oh, you'll be seeing them soon.
Perhaps you'd like to...
join your friends in
the great world beyond!
See if you can dodge this!
What the-?!
That looks like...
[Sekieki] It can't be!
Son Goku!
Tell me, is this "the great
world beyond" you mentioned?
[Jikoku] Impossible! Gah!
[Sanzo] Sure took
you long enough.
I'm sorry!
[Outo] It's not exactly
procedure to leave
my post like this,
but it would be a dereliction
of duty not to investigate.
Strange... Could they...
[Gojyo] You're not
too quick, are ya?
I thought I'd die of boredom.
[Outa] Sha Gojyo!
That's right. My
name gets around.
It looks like you're... a god.
Looks like I won't
be bored after all.
I-I can't believe I fell
for this obvious trick.
It's common for tacticians like
you to plan too well and miss
seeing the bigger picture.
[Souto] Jikoku may be dead,
but we still have the numbers.
Hold your ground!
[Hakkai] I'm sorry. I'm afraid
that's no longer the case.
[Souto] If it isn't Cho Hakkai!
How do you explain this?!
Uh, I was sure that
I had killed him!
You know wha they say, if you
ever meet a giant grizzly bear
in the forest you should just
roll over and play dead.
Least that's what I did.
Hold on! If you're not dead,
you sure did scream like
you're a little girl!
I'm sorry, but my entire plan
hinged on giving you a totally
convincing performance.
[Souto] Don't tell me the whole
thing was all a hoax so you
could assess the enemy!
[Hakkai] Well... Hakuryu
and I might have taken
a little look around.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but it looks as though
there were only five of you.
Oh haha, that's right. We
killed one, so that leaves four.
[Gojyo] I'm afraid not.
[Goku] Gojyo!
I just killed that greenhorn
back at the cliff, so...
if my math is right,
that just leaves three.
[Souto] Outo is dead too?
Ooh? So the asanine
assassins didn't kill you
after all, did they, monk?
You bastards. You had me running
all over this stupid forest.
You got a little
winded, didn't you?
That's because you
smoke way too much.
I'll snuff you out.
[Hakkai] That's not very
nice. Apologize to Gojyo.
[Ryokusho] What is
it with these guys?
It's like we're not even here.
[The Sanzo party continues
to casually chat]
[Ryokusho] I'll get
their attention!
I'll make sure
you die this time!
[Souto & Sekieki] Ryokusho!
Don't take this the wrong way,
but I don't intend to let
myself die in your arms!
Ryokusho.
Okay, I guess that's
Hakkai: 2, Grizzly bear: 0.
Damn it. And I really
wanted to waste that stupid
guy for making me run so much.
Looks like I'm left with
the crumbs as usual.
[Sekieki] Crumbs? Don't
underestimate me.
[Sekieki screams]
Hmph. That'll teach you
to overestimate yourself.
Se-Sekieki...
Uh-oh, looks like all of your
trusty little friends are gone.
You should see when
Sanzo gets really mad.
I think it's best for all
concerned to surrender quietly.
[Souto] Tell me, Genjo Sanzo,
if your friends had
truly been dead,
would you still have turned
down my offer to join Homura?
[Sanzo] Yes.
[Souto] So be it.
We were far too ambitious.
But we could no longer
serve the incompetent
heavens in good conscience.
We served Homura...
to seek our fortune!
I'm not going back!
I'll get that Scripture
if I have to kill every
last one of you!
Goku!
I'm on it!
Wipe that damn smile
off your face!
What smile's that?
[Souto] Damn you!
Stupid chimp.
What to do with him?
Heh. He's sure having fun.
But... but why?
Unlike you, I know when
it comes my time to die.
In the Heavens, we
had never known defeat.
So you must tell me...
How were you able to beat us?
What power do you have...
that allows you to
outmaneuver heaven?
All the battles
we've survived...
The fact that we're alive...
And we don't believe.
Now I see...
How stupid.
They should have known they
didn't stand a chance
against them.
It would have been considerably
worse for them to keep rotting
away in heaven.
I admire their tenacious
determination to change
their fate.
It's so much better that they
died this way, don't you think?
I'd say they did remarkably
well for common soldiers.