[Sanzo] Shit, it looks
like rain.
[Gojyo] There's got to be an inn
around here somewhere.
[Sanzo] I've got a 1000 yen
that says it starts pouring
before we find a place.
[Gojyo] You're on.
[Hakkai] That's a sissy bet.
Let's put some real money on it.
What's wrong, Goku? Have to take
a piss?
No, it's just...
I smell something weird.
[Sanzo] Yeah, something's
not right.
[Goku] Stop!
What the hell happened here?
Those talismans...
[Hakkai] Looks like I owe you a
1000 yen.
Here, I've brought everyone some
hot tea!
[Hakkai] Over there please.
You're lucky I had a last minute
vacancy, you know.
[Gojyo] This is a dump.
[Sanzo] And I thought those
demon corpses would be the
low point of the evening.
Oh, that must be Rikudo again.
[Hakkai] Rikudo?
[Goku] Who's that?
[Lady] Who's Rikudo? You guys
must be from the East,
we don't know much about him
but he's considered a savior
around here.
They say he's a monk who wanders
the country side slaying demons.
Few have ever actually seen him,
but those who have say he's 7ft
tall with talismans all over
his body.
Capable of destroying a hundred
demons at a pop.
Now if you'll excuse me, I've
got some cookies in the oven.
I'll bring you some.
[Hakkai] That'd explain the
talismans we saw on those
corpses.
[Sanzo] Those talismans, I've
seen them somewhere before.
That man?
No, it can't be.
[Gojyo] So you live here too?
Where's your room?
[Lady] Hmm, I'm not sure I
should tell you.
[Gojyo] That's okay. Ever done
it in the rain?
[Lady] [nervous] Oh, you.
[Sanzo] Shit, Gojyo! Can't I
leave you alone for one minute
without you chasing after
some tart?
[Gojyo] Don't take out your
sexual frustrations on
me, cleric!
[Sanzo] Remember the mess
you got us in after your
ast escapade?
[Gojyo] What kind of faggot
fights with a fan anyway?
[Sanzo] The kind that can kick
your ass!
How nice of you to let us stay
here for the night.
And thanks again so much for the
wonderful tea.
I promise you'll hardly even
know we're here at all.
That rain.
So familar.
[Koumyou] Rain is the bringer
of life,
yet it becomes dispiriting when
it carries on like this,
eh, Kouryuu?
[Kouryuu] I'm sure it will let
up soon, Master Sanzo.
It always does.
[Sanzo] Kouryuu, river orphen,
that's what they called me then.
[Monk 1] Here he comes again.
[Monk 2] His parents cast him
into the river the instant he
was born,
now he struts around like he
thinks he's the star pupil.
[Monk 3] I don't care how good
he is at meditation and martial
arts he'll always be a
river rat.
[Monk 1] Master always had
soft spot for lost causes.
[Monk 2] If it rains long enough
maybe we can toss him in the
water again.
See if he floats.
[Monks laugh]
[Monk 1] Owowowowow!
Shouldn't you two be attending
to your chores? Rather than
sitting around chit chatting?
Clerk Abbot!
Maybe you guys would like
to focus some of that energy
on cleaning the outhouses.
[Monk 1] Yes sir.
You haven't changed, Shuei.
Neither have you, river rat.
So, I hear your Master Sanzo's
star pupil,
one of our highest-ranking
monks, and capable of routing
a full-grown man to boot.
[Kouryuu] You should see the
weaklings they pit me against.
[Shoei] And full of
confidence too.
No wonder they're all green
with envy.
Not that you should let
that bother you.
But knowing you, it probably
doesn't at all.
Boy am I glad I'm the
Clerk Abbot.
Otherwise I might have to spar
you in practice.
[Kouryuu] Yeah, whatever.
Shuei the talisman user, the
man who went directly from
apprentice to Clerk Abbot.
There's not a monk who
doesn't know about your
talismanic powers.
Aw, flatterer.
[Shuei] Which reminds me, I hear
you're being given a holy name.
Congratulations.
[Kouryuu] It's about time.
Anything's better that Kouryuu
the river rat.
Kouryuu the river orphen.
[Shuei] Kouryuu the drift wood.
But why would you take on a holy
name if you have no intention
of ever embracing the faith?
[Kouryuu] I reserve all my faith
for Master Sanzo.
I have no place for gods.
Though I can not believe in
deities, I do believe in myself.
Master Sanzo saved my life
taking me in, but my reasons
for embracing him are not
so petty.
Sanzo is the only person I will
ever call Master.
[Shuei] How very like you.
Clerk Abbot! I've been looking
all over for you!
[Shuei] What is it?
[Monk] An enormous bear has
broken inside the compound!
It must be mad! No one is able
to stop it! What are we going
to do!
[Monk] The eyes! Aim for
the eyes!
It's fixing to attack! Get back!
Get back!
Get him out of there!
Our spears are just like twigs
against that thing
Damn it! Then I'll stop him!
[Shuei] Kouryuu?
Be calm. I can take care
of this.
Turn back. There is no food for
you here.
[Kouryuu] Listen to me, my
friend, go back and never
come back.
And we in turn will never
violate your territory.
Let us make this promise so that
we may coexisist.
Understand?
Do you understand?
[quietly] The boy's not a river
rat, he's a demon.
Only an evil spirit could
have that kind of super
natural power.
[Monk] Is something wrong,
Master Sanzo?
Nothing that wasn't expected.
[Knock at the door]
[Shuei] I'm coming in, Kouryuu.
Master Sanzo wants to see you.
Sorry, I must have spaced out
there. Say again?
I said, Master Sanzo is calling
for you.
Yes, of course.
[Shuei] Someone said you were an
evil spirit,
but just now, sitting in the
window, you looked like
something else.
The way the moon created a halo
around your golden hair,
and your eyes violet,
just like...
[Kouryuu] Shuei.
I have something for you.
[Shuei] But these are the beads
they found on you in the river.
Are you sure?
[Kouryuu] I've never given
anyone anything before.
I'm sure, but guard them well.
I promise.
[Sanzo Narrating] And so the
tranquility of the night faded.
And in the morning we woke to
a nightmare.
[Monk] Master Sanzo!
I haven't thought about that
day in years.
You had a bad dream?
[Sanzo] Yes.
I heard you wake up from the
next room.
[Sanzo] Sorry...
[Hakkai] No,
the rain also gives me a
little trouble sleeping.
[Sanzo] That's what it is then.
It's... because of the rain.
[Lady screams]
[Hakkai] It came from
he kitchen!
[Lady] Help!
[Gojyo] What's wrong?!
[Lady] A demon!
[Demon breathing loudly,
growling]
Why you bastard! How could you?!
You ate all the cookies!
Goku, look out behind you!
Eat this!
You know, I've never seen you
this active in the morning.
I have my days.
Kicking demon ass is better than
coffee for me.
That is so disgusting, man.
[Rikudo] I draw upon the power
of the talisman to banish these
demons from the world...
[Sanzo] That voice!
[Rikudo] of the living
[Rikudo] nd send them back
where they came from.
[Rikudo] Hear my name, demons,
I am Rikudo.
And I will rid the earth of
every last one of you.
I'd recognize those
beads anywhere.
Shuei!
[Lady] How can we ever thank you
so much, Master Rikudo!
[Rikudo] Slaying demons is my
only reward.
[Gojyo] This guy's Rikudo?
[Sanzo] So Shuei is the
demon slayer.
But something's changed in him.
It's as if he's suddenly taken
on an evil presence.
Whoever he is, he sure took care
of that problem for us.
That's right. Back to bed!
[Rikudo] Wait.
[Rikudo] Not all of you
are human.
[Gojyo] What?
[Hakkai] So tell me, Mr.
Brainstorm, whatever gave
you that idea?
[Rikudo] I can smell you. I can
smell your stench from here.
[Goku] You're no better roses
either, pal.
[Rikudo] You... I made a vow to
destroy ALL demon kind!
I don't think that's very nice,
you could at least get to
know us.
[Sanzo] Shuei...
Is that anyway to greet
a friend?
It can't be!
Certainly there's no point in
wasting your talent offing
these pussies.
Wait! You know him?!
[Rikudo laughs]
Funny I heard a rumor about a
renegade Sanzo priest
heading west,
never thought I'd find him and
his band of demon misfits in a
place like this.
So Kouryuu! Or I should say,
Genjo Sanzo!
Did you forget that it was
vile like that that killed
your predecessor?
Are enemies now friends?
Well, Shuei, if that's still
your name.
Did you forget what it means to
be a holy man of faith?
Shuei didn't forget!
Shuei died the day you left the
temple ten years ago!
[Shuei] Let me through!
Priest Sanzo!
Kouryuu!
What happened?!
I couldn't save him.
[Abbot] You say burglars broke
into Master Sanzo's room
last night,
murdered him and took the
Seiten Scripture?
Is this what you're saying?
Speak. Speak up child.
[Kouryuu] Yes, that's how
it happened.
My master was able to save the
Maten Scripture but it cost him
his life.
Judging from their appearence I
can only assume they were,
well, a group of demons.
[Monk A] You can't be serious!
You don't actually expect us to
believe a story like that?
More likely you killed Master
Sanzo and took the scripture
for yourself!
How dare you say something
like that!
[Kouryuu] No Shuei, it's true.
Master Sanzo is dead and one of
the temple's sacred relics,
has been stolen.
There's no excuse.
Abbott, please allow me to make
up for my negligence by granting
me leave,
so that I may avenge my master
and reclaim the Seiten
Scripture. I beg you.
[Monk A] You better not be
trying to smooth talk your way
out of this!
I admire your courage, but
everyone of use was responcible
for protecting the scriptures
while they were within the
Kinzan Temple walls.
Reclaiming them is not a burden
you should bear alone, my son.
No Abbot. I'm afraid those
sacred scriptures belong
to me now.
[Abbot] Explain.
Last night, my master bestowed
the holy name
right before he passed away.
Genjo Sanzo, that is my name
from this day forth!
[Monk A] That can't be!
He bears the crimson chakra on
his forehead,
a symbol passed down from Sanzo
to Sanzo. Only the one chosen by
Heaven may wear it.
Then this must be Buddha's will.
[Monk A] Abbott!
[Abbot] With Koumyou Sanzo's
gold crown.
I hereby recognize you as
Priest Toua Genjo Sanzo
the 31st,
formal heir to the Seiten and
Maten Scriptures,
two of the five Founding
Parchments of Heaven and Earth.
[Rikudo] In the morning, you
descended the mountain to
exact your revenge.
But that night, the demon
burglars attacked again
for the Maten Scriptures they
failed to seize before,
not knowing you had taken them
with you.
If they could defeat you and
Master Sanzo,
you can imagine what they did
to those defencless monks.
I had no choice but to use a
forbidden talisman to cast a
curse upon myself.
And acquire the power to
destroy all demons!
You- You used the Spell
of Araya?!
Of course! But once cast the
Spell of Araya can never
be reversed
and I will never again
know mercy.
The talisman starves for
the blood of demons.
Only the devouring of their dark
souls can satisfy it and ease
my suffering.
That thing has complete
control over him.
I will know only pain so long
as demons walk upon the face
of the earth.
For ten years I have murdered
their kind, innocent
or otherwise.
But now that the demons have
started attacking humans,
people have begun revering me as
some kind of hero!
[Rikudo laughs maniacally]
[Rikudo] Isn't that delicious?!
He's just crackin' himself up.
Yeah, and he calls us demons.
Shuei...
Surely you can see the talisman
has turned you into some kind
of a monster.
I'll show you just what kind of
monster I am!
[Hakkai] I think it's about time
to go.
[Goku] But it's raining!
[Gojyo] Yeah, yeah and your
point is?
[Gojyo] Man, this rain sucks!
I can't see a thing.
[Goku] Hakkai, behind you!
What?
[Rikudo] I wouldn't try that. I
can dissolve you by the mere
touch of my hand.
Let go of him, prune face!
Whoa this ground is slick.
[Goku] Well don't just
stand there.
[Rikudo] Yes, aren't you going
to help your demon friends?
No I'm not. Because you know it
doesn't really matter if I help
these guys or not,
believe me they won't
die anyway.
That's true enough.
Besides, he probably wouldn't be
praying for our souls anyway.
We'll see about that!
[Sanzo] But as great as they
are, one was greater.
[Kouyruu] What are you
doing, Master?
Shouldn't you be teaching?
Right now, I'm making
paper airplanes.
It's about the only skill I have
worth passing on to others, in
my opinion.
All I ever need to know,
I learned by folding
paper airplanes.
[Koumyou] Isn't it marvelous?
The way the orange accents the
blue and vise versa.
Because these color are
opposites each enhances what
is distinctive about the other.
Ah, a trifling thing I suppose.
[Kouryuu] Not at all.
It's beautiful.
[Sanzo] He gave me something
that day, something I wanted
to protect.
And when it was taken from me,
I learned how small I was.
I vowed to never again care for
someone so much.
I couldn't bear to lose them.
All of our spells are useless
against this guy.
None of my attacks have worked.
Any of you guys got any
bright ideas?
[Hakkai] Have we tried running
away yet?
[Sanzo] Shuei...
Your avenging days are over.
You know there is only one way
to end this curse.
[Goku] No!
[Sanzo] Get out of my way!
How can you just go and kill him
like that without thinking?
Isn't he your friend?
[Rikudo] You make me sick.
[Rikudo attacks]
[Goku] Wait... Sanzo?
[Goku] Sanzo!
Sanzo, wake up! Sanzo, wake up!
You weren't meant to die like
this! Just hold on man!
[Sanzo] At least now I know.
He can't be redeemed.
[Goku] Sanzo!
[Goku] Sanzo! I can't believe he
did this to you!
Sanzo! No!
Sanzo!
SANZO!