[laughter]
[narrator] Previously,
on Saiyuki...
[puppet] Hello. Hello.
[narrator] A puppet approached
the Sanzo party.
[puppet] Cho Gonou,
you are going to die.
Why does that toy call
you by your old name?!
[narrator] The puppet was
a shikigami sent from
Chin Yisou,
a mysterious fortune-teller
from Hakkai's past.
[gasp]
Hey Gojyo, look out!
[Hakkai] Gojyo!
[Gojyo] Ya little...
Tru-
[Sanzo] Come on out, Chin Yisou.
Well my goodness.
Don't we look dashing?
[narrator] Chin Yisou did
not aim to kill Hakkai,
but to destroy his spirit.
Hey, that's really low!
Because next time, he really is
going to lose some of his little
play buddies.
You just try it.
[Goku] Battle Against Darkness
[Goku] What's going on?
Why isn't either one
of them moving?
[Sanzo] They're both
looking for an opening.
[Goku] Hey, you dirty
old bastard!
[Chin] Hmm?
[Goku] Yeah, you!
You just try and do
something to Sanzo!
My compliments,
your pet is quite
a loyal companion,
I have to say.
Goku, stand back!
He howls too much for my tastes.
Awful lot of bark for a mutt
who can barely stand up
on his own two paws.
[Gojyo] Dude, you really
have a broken leg?
[Goku] I told you that already!
[Hakkai] Sanzo, let's split
up while he's not looking.
Yes, good idea.
Gojyo's probably hasn't
fully recovered yet and
I'm betting Goku isn't
at his best either.
Ready?
Go!
Cowards!
Attacking me while
my back is turned!
All right, so it's my turn now!
We're going after him!
Gojyo, you stay here with Goku.
[Gojyo] Wait a minute!
I can't believe those
bastards ditched us!
[Goku] Are we going
to take that from them?
[Gojyo] It won't be easy
to defeat that guy on their own.
Let's go after them!
[Goku] I'm right behind you!
I take it your wound's
not completely healed yet?
Useless bastard.
Oh, you're sure one to talk,
you stupid one-legged monkey!
Quit calling me a monkey,
water sprite!
We haven't lost sight
of him, have we?
No, I'm sensing something else.
[Hakkai] Chin Yisou,
if you want to kill me,
you'll have to show
yourself eventually!
[Sanzo] He's sure to be around
here somewhere.
At the moment, he's planning
to have you watch me die
right in front of your eyes.
[Hakkai] No.
That's not what he's after.
He wants to destroy
my soul, Sanzo.
[Chin] I'm so happy for you.
Her suffering has finally
come to an end.
My goodness,
what a terrifying look.
You must...
[choking]
be desiring to murder me
with all your heart and soul.
[Chin] How proud you must be
to have slayed ever demon in
this castle all by yourself.
No human could have accomplished
a feat like that all alone.
[Chin] Then again...
it is only a legend, but it says
a human who has bathed in the
blood of a thousand demons
shall become a demon himself.
Isn't that ironic?
[Hakkai] B-Bastard!
I was sure I had killed
him that night.
But there's no mistaking
those eyes.
[clink]
Sanzo...
[Sanzo] What is it?
Ask me something stupid,
and I'll kill you.
[Hakkai] Okay,
maybe I shouldn't, then.
[Sanzo] Are you trying
to annoy me?
Do you think...
it's really okay
for me to be here?
[Sanzo] See? That was stupid.
Now I have to kill you.
[Hakkai] Is it really?
[Sanzo] I know you
would never betray me.
Am I right?
That's not a fair
question, it is?
[Hakkai] I've never really been
in a position to find out.
[Goku] Arg, that branch
just hit me in the face!
[Gojyo] Will you stop
struggling?
You can't even
stand by yourself!
[Goku] Can't you go any faster?
[Gojyo] Stop your whining!
I need to concentrate
on where I'm going.
[Goku] In circles,
it looks like.
Do we even know that Hakkai
and Sanzo went this way?
It's Hakkai's mental state
I'm worried about.
Oh, I'm sure
he'll be all right, man.
[Goku] He told me that as long
as there are people out there
who believe in him,
he'll find a way to survive.
He'll do anything within his
power not to let them down.
[Gojyo] Yeah, but he said that
before he had a crazy fortune
teller trying to kill him.
I'm sure he'll be all right.
[Gojyo] Hold on,
I'm speeding up, money-boy!
[Goku] Stop calling
me that, water sprite!
He's on the move now.
Up there!
[Chin] Heh, heh, heh. How sweet.
A little heart-to-heart
before the big farewell.
I'm through with playing this
game of hide-and-seek with you.
Come down here!
Is that so, monk?
Then I'll take as little
of your time as possible.
This will all be over quickly.
[Chin] Cho Gonou,
you killed my entire clan
for the sake of one woman.
I hope she was worth it.
For one single woman who
was my entire other life.
[Chin] Not only did you
kill my entire clan,
but you had the audacity
to kill my father.
He died by your hands, no?
You're breaking my heart.
[Chin] Oh, what a forgiving
friend you have there,
Cho Gonou.
I can't tell you how
happy it makes me to see
that you have found
another companion
who you would just
hate to see die.
I'm the one you're after,
so go ahead and try to do
whatever you can to me,
but him...
I will personally see to
it that you never lay
a finger on him!
Heh, heh, heh.
I can't lay a finger
on the monk, you say?
[laughter]
[Chin] But how will I kill him?
Oh, what to do? What to do?
Quite a predicament.
Tell you what...
[Chin] Hakkai, you do take
care of the monk for me.
I want to see your face...
[Chin] Show me the agony
you suffer at witnessing
your own crime!
[Hakkai] No, this can't be...
[screaming]
What is it?
[Hakkai] Stay back.
Please, don't come near me.
[Sanzo] Hakkai! Hakkai-
Hakkai...
[Hakkai] I can't control my arm.
[Chin] What a frail
creature you are.
How easily I was able to work
my way into the crevices
of your heart.
Now, hurry up and put him
out of his misery.
[Hakkai] Never!
Why on Earth not?
Can't you see that the poor
boy is suffering because of you?
[Chin] It should be easy. Think
of all the practice you've had.
Just let go and do as you've
done so many times before!
What's one more death
considering all the others
who have died at your hands?
[screaming]
Hakkai!
What the hell's going on?!
[Gojyo] Hey,
don't over exert yourself-
Hey, I'll pull my weight!
That'll be a change.
[Chin] Ah, the memories.
I can't tell you how nice it is
for us to reminisce like this.
Surely you remember the night...
I died?
So...
Now you truly have...
become a demon like us.
[screaming]
[Hakkai] How can you be alive?
I killed him! I know I did!
Yes, you did a fine job
of slicing into me.
You must have had quite
a bit of practice,
being the man who became one
of us by bathing in the blood
of a thousand demons you slayed.
But that night, as I breathed
my last, I took this life piece,
and buried it deep inside
my dying body
through the opening you
carved into my gut.
[Hakkai] My gut?
This psycho turned his own
corpse into a shikigami!
[Chin] Do you know what posessed
me to do such a terrible thing
to myself?
I did it so that one day,
I could make you suffer.
So that one day,
you could feel the pain I felt.
It can't be...
[Chin] Lose a little bit
of what I lost...
[Hakkai] No!
[Chin] ...until I take away
everything you cared for.
[screaming]
[Hakkai] Sanzo...
Sanzo!
Sanzo! Sanzo!
[screaming]
See how easy that was?
And I didn't even have
to lift a finger.
[Goku] Sanzo!
[Chin] Look, your friends
have arrived.
I guess you'll have a hard
time explaining what you did.
Not much longer, now.
[Chin] Soon, you will
have nothing left.
[Goku] What's happened here?
Sanzo?
[Gojyo] Is he all right?
We aren't too late, are we?
What did that bastard do?
[Hakkai] I did it.
[Goku] What?!
[Gojyo] Come again?
[Hakkai] I did it!
Look out!
What're you doing, Hakkai?!
It's really no use.
He might as well be
my own personal puppet.
Stop it! Hakkai!
Get out of the way, Goku!
[Chin] Hrg!
No!
It was all part
of some stupid act?
Don't play us for fools, moron.
Wait a sec... you were just
faking the whole time?
I should've known after
that performance.
Don't quit your day job.
[Sanzo] Bite me.
[Hakkai] Didn't mean
to scare you.
I have to admit, I actually
kind of enjoyed the show.
[Chin] I have to agree,
quite a spectacle.
Hakkai would probably rather
bite off his own tongue
than strangle me to death.
You said it was easy to find
the crevices in my heart?
[Hakkai] Well, my heart isn't
big enough for crevices.
You would think you would've
learned after the last time
I killed you,
not to underestimate me,
fortune teller.
The only difference between
you and the rest of your clan...
is that I get to kill you twice.
[laughter]
[Gojyo] What's so damn funny?!
[Chin] I don't mind dying,
but do you actually think
you can defeat me with
Qigong techniques?
Do you?
[Chin] Or perhaps...
you are brave enough
to fight without your
demon power limiters,
as you did then?!
I see no need for
something so rash.
Oh?!
[Chin] Have you lost your mind?!
[Hakkai] It was right
about here, wasn't it?
Where I stabbed you
all those years ago.
Your Qigong is not powerful
enough to hurt me...
[Hakkai] Oh, I don't know.
You'd be surprised.
Qigong can actually
be quite versitle.
[Chin] I'm so
disappointed in you.
I expected you to provide much
more entertainment than you did.
[Hakkai] Thank you very much.
Guess I didn't do a very good
job of following your script.
[Chin] Cho Gonou...
[Hakkai] No...
[groan]
My name is Cho Hakkai.
How every ounce
of my being despises you.
[Chin] Even in the end,
I hate you.
What a coincidence. I feel
the exact same way about you.
[Hakkai] At least I'm not
a creature like you,
without a past or a future.
[Goku] You pervery
water sprite!
What do you think you're doing?!
Cut it out!
[Gojyo] Ooh, I like it.
[Goku] I can't walk around
with all this graffiti!
It's insulting!
[Sanzo] Will you shut up?!
Can you at least just be quiet
while we set you leg?!
[Goku] Now my head bone's broke!
Try breaking his jaw bone, huh?
I'm already one step
ahead of you, my man.
[Goku] Don't even joke about it!
[Gojyo] Heh, heh, heh.
You know, I enjoyed that.
You're awfully energetic.
Shouldn't you be recovering
from your injuries?
You're sure one to talk.
You look as though a weight's
been lifted off your shoulders.
I suppose.
You know, in a funny way,
that fortune teller did
me a huge favor.
[Hakkai] I've been carrying my
past around with me so long.
I suppose it was only
a matter of time...
before I had to confront
that part of myself again.
Right now, I'm wishing my
lifeline was just a teensy
bit longer
than it is at the moment.
Yeah?
Guess that means that
I just have to get used
to the idea
that I'm going to have to make
the most of the short time
that I have left.
[Goku] No.
I've got a better idea!
Try this!
Yeah?
Dumbass. Can't you at least
pick up after yourself?
[Goku] That hurt!
[Gojyo] Heh, heh, heh.
Do it again.
[Hakkai] Kanan, I'd like
to live for myself
just a little while longer.
[Hakkai] Ah...
[Gojyo] Huh?
[Hakkai] This is permanent ink.
[Gojyo] Yup, permanent ink.
[Hakkai] Will you look at that?
It's not going to come off.
Nope, not coming off.
I guess that's all right.
[Sanzo] Everybody,
let's move out!
[Gojyo] Right with you!
[Goku] Maybe if we had steak,
my bones would heal quicker?
[Sanzo] Like hell they would!
[Goku] You've heard the
saying that you shouldn't
trust anybody,
but does that mean we should
even be suspicious of the people
we're close to?
I can't do that!
Even if others
do think I'm stupid,
you've got to have
faith in people!
Otherwise, how can you
have faith in yourself?
Or the future?
Trust is put to the test
in "The Forbidden Fruit",
next time on "Saiyuki".