[Hakkai] Hold in there, Hakuryu.
We need to make it through this
pass by the end of the day.
[Hakuryu squeaks, while
Goku's stomach rumbles loudly]
[Goku] I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
I'm freezing and hungry.
I'm freezing and hungry,
and freezing and hungry,
and freezing and hungry!
Freezing and hungry, freezing
and hungry, freezing and hungry.
Shut the hell up. You're
just making things worse.
You're the one who said
to go this way, you
non-directional jackass!
Let's not go digging
up the past, shall we?
[Mocking Gojyo] Ooh,
let's go this way, guys!
Shut up, stupid monkey.
[Goku] What the hell's going
on?! Why aren't we moving?!
It looks like this is as far
as Hakuryu's going to go.
You're joking!
[Hakuryu squeaks]
[Goku] "Shed No Tears".
[Gojyo] Whatever I
did to deserve this
misery, I apologize.
I hope you're warm enough.
[Hakuryu squeaks in reply]
[Goku] I'm exhausted.
Get up or I'll stomp you.
So tired.
Will you stop fooling
around and get the
hell up, ya lazy bum?!
[Hakkai] This is strange.
[Gojyo] Huh?
You must mean the fact that he's
complaining about something
besides being hungry.
[Hakkai] No. It's this blizzard.
It seems unseasonably
harsh for this time of
year. Don't you think so?
So it's an ambush,
is it? How quaint.
I know I could use
a little warm up.
[Shoryu] Took you
guys long enough.
I've been waiting all day.
[Gojyo] I'm sorry, did
we have an appointment?
It would have been better
if you died in the blizzard.
Since you've come this far...
Oh well, I guess I'll
have to use force.
Why would that be?
[Shoryu] Because, I intend
to take the Maten Scripture.
[Hakkai] I assume this
storm is your doing as well?
More or less.
Did I hit you too hard?
It's a little trick
I've been working on.
Haven't used it much.
Awesome! That kicked ass!
Tell me! What's your name?
It's Shoryu.
And the next time,
I'll hit you harder.
Huh?! What the-?!
What did ya do, ya brat?!
Just giving you
the cold shoulder.
Using some kind of weirdass
voodoo aren't ya, ya
little son of a bitch?
Well, you're gonna regret it!
Why would I regret it?
I have no place in my life
for such things as regret.
That's not good.
Awesome! Check those out!
Dumb brat, you need
some discipline.
I need the Scripture.
All you're getting from
me, spike boy, is lead.
What?!
[Koushu] So, how
are you feeling?
I so adore willful children.
I have a favor to ask.
You don't mind running a little
errand for me, do you, darling?
I want the Maten and
Seiten Scripture.
You got that?
Such a good boy.
Now get going.
[Sanzo] Brat!
Damn, I can't believe
I missed him!
If you're a good little boy
and you do exactly what I
say, I'll set you free.
Hahaha. And because I like
you so much, I'll even give
you a good luck charm.
[Shoryu screams in pain]
That should make you brave,
and don't come back here...
until you've finished
your chores.
[Gojyo] Think we got 'em?
[Sanzo] No.
[Hakkai] What do you think
made him heistate like that?
Oh wow, did you see
'em? Those blades?
Shit man, those
are awesome! Sweet!
[Sanzo] Stupid monkey.
Boy, that smarts!
What'd he do that for?
Those blades are not to
be admired. Not at all.
Huh?
That boys' blades...
are forbidden magic, Goku.
[Koushu] Aah Shoen, you have no
idea how much trouble I went
through to get that charm.
My brother...
I'm sure that he will
succeed, my lady.
[Koushu] You think so, huh?
I do.
[Koushu] My, aren't
you a smart one?
[Shoen] Forgive me! I
did not mean to sound...
It's quite alright.
Honestly, I wasn't talking
about him anyway.
But we three are like family.
Don't you worry. I
have plans for Shoryu.
And after all I've done
for the both of you...
I expect you'll be
indebted to me for life.
But master...
[Koushu] What is it?
[Shoen] You promised...
[Koushu] Oh, please!
You didn't actually
believe me, did you?
I was obviously joking.
What a fool.
You know how much technology
I've invested in you?
How charmingly naive.
Well then.
Since Shoryu seems to be
having such a hard time of it,
perhaps I'll send you to Homura.
If I may, please...
I would very much like to have a
charm like Shoryu, Lady Koushu.
[Koushu] No. One charm
is more than adequate.
Believe me, it works
better that way.
You two. Tell me,
what are your names?
Shy, are we? Then I'll
just have to come up with
names for you on my own.
You are my very own
children now, after all.
[Homura] Not here either.
What is it?
I'm busy.
You are the War Prince,
are you not?
Did no one ever
teach you manners?
You must introduce yourself
to me first, my dear.
[Shoen] I have no
need for a name.
Do you have some
business with me?
[Shoen] My business is
with the Seiten Scripture.
That is impossible.
All the same.
Try it.
[Hakkai] That power...
Do you think it could really
be forbidden magic after all?
[Sanzo] Possibly.
Tell me, tell me!
What is this magic?
Goku, I know that you've
heard about this before.
There's certain types of magic
that are strictly forbidden.
[Goku] But why?
Well, that's because... Uh...
Shut up and walk.
Try moving your legs instead
of your mouth, huh?
What's the deal?! Why
can't you answer me, huh?
It's just a stupid question.
[Hakkai] Hmm.
[Sanzo] Sure is a
persistant little tyke.
[Hakkai & Gojyo] Huh?
[Gojyo] You...
And quite a little
trouble maker.
Oh, I've just begun
making trouble.
[Sanzo] What do you want the
Maten Scripture for anyway?
[Shoryu] That's for me to
know and you to find out.
You'll hand it over if you
know what's good for you.
[Gojyo] Don't be stupid.
Pick a fight with us...
And we'll kick your ass!
Even if you are a kid!
Well, that wasn't
much fun at all.
[Homura] Now, I like you.
That's quite a spell
you have there.
Tell me, what's your name?
I believe I asked
you a question.
My name is...
Stand back!
Will you serve me?
Serve you?
I could certainly use
a spell like that.
Why don't you fight on my side?
[Koushu] Poor things.
You should have listened to me.
You know what happens
to children who won't
obey, don't you?
I'm sure you'll both
be good from now on.
Don't you dare leave here
again without my permission.
There. Understand me?
Because you better.
Jeez... This little
kid is powerful!
[Hakkai] Sanzo...
[Hakuryu squeaks]
Why do you persist on fighting?
The Maten Scripture
isn't worth crap to you.
[Shoryu] I don't
care what it's for.
Then why do you want it?
So I can be free again.
Now tell me what you're
here for, my friend.
Answer me!
[Shoen] I won't...
I WON'T!
It would be a shame to kill
a child of such promise.
No matter who you serve.
Begone, and I'll overlook this.
[Shoryu] It'll be okay!
I'll be back soon!
I promise!
[Shoryu] Stop laughing!
[Sanzo] Not only are you a brat,
but you're a fool on top of it.
Open your eyes.
Shut up!
It's... already too late.
[Homura] You won't
get a second chance.
If only I had acted earlier...
If only I had acted earlier
before it was too late.
[Shoen screams]
Dumbass. What you're searching
so hard for is not someone
else's to give, I'm afraid.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I never had anyone around to
teach me things like that.
Of course you didn't. Now
stop whining, you crybaby.
Enough of this.
I'm through playing
around with you, kid.
You want your freedom?
Then live.
[Shoryu crying]
[Hakkai] Sanzo...
[Goku] Did he...
What did that little
brat do this time, huh?
I guess... he chose to be free.
He must think...
eternal freedom can
be found in Heaven.
I told you he was a stupid brat.
[Koushu] Where are they?
I guess I wasn't strict
enough with them.
Oh well. I'll change that.
Shoen!
Hello?! Anyone here?!
Why won't anyone answer ME?!