[Hakkai] What's with
everyone today?
I don't think I've ever
seen you so quiet.
[Gojyo] Come on, we've had our
share of downtimes, haven't we?
[Hakkai] If you've suddenly
decided to play the part
of the brooding artist,
it doesn't suit you.
[Gojyo] Stop it. You're making
me feel all fuzzy inside.
[Hakkai] You know, if
you insist on keeping this
somber attitude of yours,
that neighbor of yours
is going to get bored.
Isn't that right, Goku?
Goku?
What's wrong?
You eat something that
didn't agree with you?
I'll be damned...
He's sleeping with
his eyes open.
That's just too goddamn creepy!
[Sanzo] Shut up
or I'll kill you!
That's too weird.
Sanzo shouts in his sleep.
[Goku] "The Real Imposters."
[Fake Sanzo] Welcome!
How would you like to
try some tasty noodles?
[Customer 1] Oh, great!
Uh, three orders please!
[Fake Hakkai] Thanks for
waiting. Would you like
some stir fried cabbage?
[Customer 2] Oh that sounds
good. Let me have two orders
of that on the side.
[Fake Sanzo] Thank you!
Please come again!
Welcome, welcome!
Thank you! Be with you in a sec!
Uuh, what would you like?
So how long have we been here?
Three months now?
Yeah. Two months and
twenty-seven days since
you and I started
this stupid job.
Can you believe it's
been that long since we
impersonated the Sanzo party?
Do you remember that?
[Fake Sanzo] Running into
the real Sanzo party was
especially horrible.
[Fake Hakkai] Yeah, it's
a miracle we're alive.
But now, you and I
are working real jobs.
Aren't we the luckiest
guys in the whole world?
Nothing can beat a good day's
hard, honest labor, can it?
You know, you and I did some
reckless things in our day.
It's kinda hard to believe
how much we've settled down.
[Goku] Excuse me!
Four noodles, please.
Make it quick!
Yes, right away, sir!
What's your problem?
[Fake Sanzo] I could
never forget those faces!
[Fake Hakkai] They've come
back to finish the job!
[Fake Sanzo] Please
don't kill us!
[Fake Hakkai] We make an
honest living now! Honest!
They're sure acting strangely.
I wonder what has
them so spooked.
Excuse me, but I believe you are
supposed to great your guest.
Am I right?
[Both Fakes] O-of course!
Hey. You don't think
they... don't know...
Who we are? I hope not.
Fried noodles! Right now!
[Both Fakes] Right!
It's yours! Free!
[Gojyo] Hey.
[Fake Sanzo] Y-yes?
[Gojyo] You're not planning
to serve us those reheated
noodles, right?
You're not really planning
to serve us these reheated
noodles, am I right?
[Fake Sanzo] Uh, wh-what are you
talking about? I made these just
a moment ago. Honestly!
[Gojyo] You're not planning
to serve us these reheated
noodles, right?!
No way! L-look here!
A fresh batch! Right?
Ah-huh, ah-huh!
I-I was just moving those
boxes to make room, honest!
[Goku] Oh, I want
an extra serving!
[Gojyo] And make the noodles
a bit on the firm side.
[Hakkai] And go heavy
on the wasabi, please!
[Sanzo] I don't care how you
make them, just hurry up!
[Fake Hakkai] H-here you
go. Thanks for waiting!
Noodles, noodles, noodles!
Thanks, I'm so glad you like
them. Please come again.
[Sanzo] Hey.
[Fake Hakkai] Yes, Sir?
I am assuming...
ginger comes with that?
[Goku] This isn't bad!
[Gojyo] Can't you wait
[Gojyo] until we get back
before you start eating?
[Goku] I can eat when I want to!
[Gojyo] Doesn't make
you any less stupid.
Safe at last.
We can both relax now.
It looks like they're leaving.
I can't believe the absolutely
incredible deal I found on
fajita skirt steak.
I think the guys're gonna be
really excited about it.
Hey, jackass! Look
where you're going!
I'm sorry! I hope you're
not hurt or anything.
Oops, looks like
you dropped this.
Here you go. You need any
help carrying them home?
Ah... ah.... ah... ah...
What's with that guy?
Uh, well. I'm not sure.
[Fake Goku] So, doing
anything later?
Whaddya say we go out tonight?
[Lady] Sorry, I have plans.
In that case, how
about tomorrow?
[Lady] I'm sorry, I don't think
you heard me the first time.
I have plans.
There must be some
time that you're free.
[Lady] Why don't you put some of
that energy into actually doing
some work around here?
What's the point? No one ever
checks into this place. Huh?!
Hey! Any rooms?
[Lady] Sure do!
Can you show these
four gentlemen...
Hello?
Now where did he run off to?
Looks like I'll be
registering you today.
If you could, just sign
here in the guestbook.
What are they doing here?
[Fake Sanzo is throwing a
fit, while Fake Hakkai and
Fake Gojyo try to restrain him]
What the hell's
going on in here?!
Well it's about damn
time you got back!
Get your ass over here!
They're back! They've come
back! Please don't hurt me!
[Fake Goku] Don't tell me
you saw the four horsemen
of the apocalypse!
[Fake Gojyo] You saw them too?!
Please don't hurt me. Why
are you doing this to me?
I must have done something
terribly, terribly wrong.
Is it because I'm worthless?
That's it. That's
the reason for it.
They forced him to make
fried noodles and they
didn't even pay.
You should have been
there, it was awful.
Poor guy. I guess it was
just too much for him to
handle. He just snapped.
I haven't seen anybody lose
it like this since my brother
told my mother he was gay.
[Fake Hakkai] I'm not sure
I could ever cook again
if they did that to me.
[Fake Gojyo] Listen you
guys, I've been thinking.
It's probably a good idea to
lay low for a couple of days.
[Fake Hakkai] Yeah, there's
no point in tempting fate.
I can't believe you!
Don't tell me you're gonna
let them get away with this!
We have no choice.
What would you have us
do? Fight them head on?
We'll get our asses kicked.
There's no way in hell
we could ever beat them.
What is this?! Don't you
guys have any self-esteem?!
Once upon a time, the four of
us were a first rate imposters!
Now look what we've become!
A bunch of sniveling
dead beat, self-pitying
losers, that's what!
They're too strong...
You can count me out...
I can't...
[Fake Goku] Okay, fine.
If that's the way you're
going to be about it...
I'll do it by myself.
This rice is absolutely awesome!
The soup was good, but the
noodles are just pure heaven!
This meal's the best!
How would I know? You pig.
You gobbled up every single
one of the dishes before
I got to try any of them.
Fine, don't talk to me. I didn't
want to talk to you anyway.
[Gojoy] Hey, gimme
back my dumpling!
[Gojyo] If you got the noodles,
then I get the dumplings!
[Goku[ No way! I was saving
them for last! Hand them over!
You thieving water sprite!
[Gojyo] If you want it so
bad, why don't you come
over here and take it!
[Goku] Okay, I will!
EW, gross! You licked it!
[Gojyo] Still want it?
[Goku spits on the dumplings]
[Goku] There, now
it's all yours!
[Gojyo] You spit
on my dumplings!
[Goku] Now neither
of us get any!
[Gojyo] Great. Now we paid
all that money for nothing!
I'm so worthless.
How about I shove it
down your throat?!
[Goku] Might be difficult
with my staff up your ass!
[Sanzo] Do you wanna see
what it's like to die?!
I'll pass on that one.
[Sanzo] What's wrong?
Huh? Oh. Nothing.
Where have I seen
those guys before?
How strange. The sky
seems so enormous today.
Why does this town
seem so surreal?
I work and I work, but what
do I have to show for it?
Life sure was easier back then.
My goodness. Sure
brings me back.
[All chatting away]
[Fake Sanzo] Get it away!
Get it away! I hate frogs!
[The frog croaks]
I hereby give blessings
on all you good people.
Oh boy. I told myself
I'd never do this again.
Okay then...
At least I'll go out
with a little...
pizzazz. A little style.
Yeah.
Look here, if it isn't
the big show off.
What's up, man?
Gojyo!
[Fake Hakkai] I couldn't have
you forgetting about me.
Mmmm. Tasty.
Hakkai...
[Fake Sanzo] Looks
like everyone's here.
I have to be honest
just a little.
Been so long, I'd almost
forgot how to wear these.
Sa-Sanzo?!
Hey, hey, hey. Don't cry.
It seems we're just not
comfortable as ourselves,
unless we're posing
as someone we're not.
[Fake Hakkai] Let's go and show
them who the real imposters are!
Let me speak!
I know... now that it...
it would have been a suicidal
mission to go up against them
and face them alone.
But I know together.. that
we can find a way to defeat
those self-righteous bastards.
Listen, I have an idea.
Yanno, it's just crazy
enough to work.
I really think you're
onto something there.
And then what we do
for the grand finale...
It's a completely airtight
plan, if ya ask me.
[Fake Goku] Everyone,
take your positions!
[All] Go!
[Gojyo] Sanzo...
It appears we have guests.
They attack in the dead of
night, so our guard's down.
The same ol' song and dance.
Sounds like there's more
than one of them this time.
[Gojyo] I was dreaming about
that girl. They are so dead.
Three little...
meat dumplings...
Hold it right
there, Sanzo party!
Pay your ticket!
Grow up, you lazy shoplifters!
That one looked up my skirt!
[The crowd complains further]
What is this crap?
I believe they must have
mistaken us for someone else.
Come back, my sweet
little dumpling...
[Sanzo] Wake up,
you stupid monkey!
[The Fake Sanzo party
laughs triumphantly]
[Fake Sanzo] It couldn't
have gone better!
I bet they're getting their
asses beat in jail right now.
[Fake Gojyo laughs] No matter
what mischief we get into,
they get to pay for it.
How do you like that?!
[Fake Sanzo] I feel like we're
getting to start all over again.
You know, it's too bad we
can't go back and eat at
that absolutely scrumptious
noodle house again.
Their dumplings were superb,
best I ever tasted.
[Goku] Damn it! I wanted
to eat those dumplings!
[All] Oh my god! It's them!
But how did they...?!
You four idiots
speak so loudly,
we could hear you all
the way from town.
We've told you. It's pretty
dangerous to be the Sanzo party.
How dare you losers
try to frame us?
You're really asking for it.
[All] Oh please! Have mercy!
You fakers!
[Sounds of the Fake Sanzo
party being beaten to a pulp]
[Gojyo] Beating up weaklings
leaves a bad taste in my mouth.
I feel like a bully.
[Goku] I could've enjoyed it
more if I weren't so hungry.
Am I alive?
I guess that the gods do exist.
I thought that we were
all goners for sure.
That's it for me. I'm
praying from now on.
Yanno, you guys, it's not so
bad the second time. Ah ha.
[Man] Don't think you
can get off that easy!
I'm telling you for
the last time, pay up!
[Storekeeper] You're paying
for everything you stole
from me, ya got that?!
Do ya know what we do
to perverts like you?!
[All] Oh please, have mercy!
[Sounds of the Fake Sanzo party
getting beaten to a bigger pulp]
[Man] That'll be the last
time they show their ugly
mugs around here.
[Cook] We won't go
so easy on them.
[The villager's chatting
begins to fade out]
Are you... guys still alive?
I'm not sure...
I think I broke something
really important.
Yes, but... don't you guys
feel like you were yourselves
again? I know I do.
I'll have to agree
with ya there.
I have to tell ya. I think in
the end, doing an honest day's
work just doesn't suit us.
I guess life is more fun when
there's some element of risk
involved, don't you think?
No matter how petty you
think your life is, you can
never lose your inner pride.
I know I will always be just an
imposter, but I'm as proud as
the real Hakkai could ever be.
What the hell was that for?!
I was just starting to
feel better, ya jerk!
[Kougaiji] Sorry, I didn't see
you lying there in the dark.
Yeah right, that's
real funny, man.
You should watch where
you're going, jackass.
We're the legendary Sanzo party.
Demons run fleeing, barefoot
at the mere sound of our name.
Scared now?
So... Sanzo party, huh?
[All] Uh-have mercy!
[Sounds of the Fake Sanzo party
being beaten to a final pulp]
What a waste of my time.
That's so weird!
I could have sworn I smelled
the real Sanzo around here.
[Kougaiji] Hurry yp.
Their idiocy may be contagious.
It...
hurts so much...
I almost don't care
about pride anymore.
Given the choice between
life and pride, life.
Life is more important.
It's better to be alive.
Hakkai, you okay?
Ugh... If I make it
through this time...
I say we don't dress
up like this...
ever again.
[All] Agreed.