[Elder] It is an age of
suffering and dispair.
Demons appear out of the
darkness to terrorize the land.
And people search for escape,
as the Earth plunges into chaos.
But just when all hope appears
to be lost, a single shaft of
light shines from the East,
and a young man appears with a
holy scripture draped around
his shoulders as a vestment
and s crimson chakra upon
his brow.
With three friends at his side,
he combats demons.
And fights to restore
tranquility to this world.
This is an ancient legend passed
down through the ages.
[Kid A] What is the
savior's name?
The name of the man is
Priest Sanzo.
Sanzo?
He is the one who read from the
holy scripture
that defeated the demons
plaguing the villagers,
those many years ago.
Do you think maybe- Do you think
the man might ever come to our
village again?
If our village were ever to fall
into trouble anew, I have a
feeling he will return.
[Fake Hakkai] They're like puddy
in our hands.
"Fake Saviors"
[Goku] Sanzo, I'm hungry!
[Gojyo] Day in and day out,
it's always the same thing,
"I'm hungry, I'm hungry."
Can't you say anything else, you
one trick monkey?
Hey you lay off, long hair!
At least I don't have a grotto
for brains, you sissy
water sprite!
Grotto, huh? That's a pretty big
word for a monkey!
I bet you don't even know what
it means.
[Goku] I do too know what
it means!
Oh, really? Then let's hear it.
Well? Come on.
I'm listening.
Sanzo...
Please, just kill me.
What? What are you doing? Are
you saying something behind
my back?
[Sanzo] I'm staying out of this.
[Goku] But Sazno! You said Gojyo
had a brain like a grotto.
[Gojyo] And you call yourself
a monk.
[Sanzo] I meant it in the nicest
possible way.
[Hakkai] Hey we're coming up
on village.
[Hakkai] So could you be on your
best behavior? Please?
[Goku] and so when you called
him a troglodyte, that meant...
[Gojyo] That does it!
Now I'm angry!
[Goku and Gojyo fighting]
[Goku] Food, food! Every where
I look it's food!
[Goku] I'm gonna eat that
and that!
[Hakkai] We ought to be able to
find a place
[Goku] And that! And that!
[Hakkai] to sleep around here
no problem.
And then it's just a matter of
finding someone to sleep
around with.
[Kid] Ow!
I'm sorry. We were just playing
tag and I guess I just
fell dow-...
[Hakkai] Are you okay? You know,
you should really be careful.
He's dressed in white, with a
scripture draped around
his shoulders...
And clear, blue eyes...
Oh my god! You're Priest Sanzo!
[Cheif] Quiet everyone.
Oh Priest Sanzo, I can't tell
you how pleased we are that you
came back to you humble village.
[Hakkai] Excuse me, I'm sorry,
but what are you talking about?
Oh yes, uh let me explain.
It was your friend Sanzo who
came to save our village,
let's see uh...
Some four hundred years ago.
And now to our great delight,
he has returned.
You honor us with your presence.
That's funny, I would have
guessed you were much younger
than that.
That's because I am.
The name Sanzo has been passed
down from generation to
generation, Goku.
We were not able to thank Priest
Sanzo properly back then,
and we vowed that we would make
it up to him if he ever returned
to our village.
So please, anything our people
can offer you is yours.
I see. I understand
your gratitude.
Well then...
But, while this all very kind
of you-
The Great Sanzo says he
welcomes your hospitality.
And the priest is
awfully hungry!
[muffled] Greedy bastards.
Yes, why of course, sir.
[Goku & Gojyo] Hold it!
Uh is there more?
Sanzo wants steak and plenty
of alcohol!
And to be waited on by pretty
young virgin maidens. Oh yeah.
Oh, and seems to be asking for a
nice warm bed too.
[Sanzo] [muffled] I'll
kill them!
[Chief] Of course, we will take
care of it right away.
Boy, you really look upset.
Relax. Think of all the guilt
these people no longer have to
live with for not having
thanked you properly.
[Sanzo] Damn narcissists.
Sure, this is nice for a while
but then there's the aftermath.
Oh such as?
[Sanzo] The nagging. The begging
for me to give them advice and
counsel them,
all for a measley meal and a
decent night's rest.
Sure, that's bad for you, but I
fail to see the downside for
the rest of us.
[Door opens]
Hey! Listen up, imposters, your
little charade is finished!
Stop this silly game of yours,
because the real and authentic
Sanzo party has arrived!
[Fake Hakkai] Well?!
[All three laugh]
Hey stop laughing!
Do you have any idea who
this is?!
It's none other than the famous
and legendary Sanzo!
Show some respect!
[Laughter continues]
I can't breathe! Make them stop!
Make them stop!
Will you get a load of this guy?
He's hilarious!
Look two Hakkai's but
three chins.
I don't know, this one looks
more like a princess than
a priest.
Stop making fun of us you fakes!
You're the real imposters!
Excuse me? Who's the half-
assed knockoff?
Alright, let's see who's
the fake!
[Sanzo] Don't!
It's not worth the effort,
my friend.
I-I- don't understand. Wh-What
the hell's going on in here?
Two Sanzos?
What just happened?
Well, apparently it looks we
didn't do a very good job of
being ourselves.
I didn't even get my dinner.
At least they won't be pestering
me to solve all of their
problems for them.
Come on! You just can't admit
you're the one who screwed
this up.
This is your fault!
Say that again.
Calm down! I mean what's the use
in fighting about it now?
At least we have beds to
sleep on.
[All three] Beds huh?
[Cheif] I am so sorry. Those
imposters nearly fooled us.
How we could have mistaken
such a sorry lot for you
fine gentlemen,
it simply defies all
explination.
We will execute them imediatly
for their crimes!
Oh, no, that's not necessary.
It happens all the time, you
wouldn't believe.
My goodness, Priest Sanzo,
that's so forgiving.
I sure wish those charlatans
could witness your fine
generostiy.
[stomach growls]
[quietly] Geeze! Can't you put
a lid on that stomach of yours?
You'll blow our cover!
You know, it might be a good
idea to pick it up a bit.
Cut to the chase.
[quietly] Mhm, got it.
[Clears throat]
Chief, considering the long and
difficult journey my comrades
and I have embarked on...
I was wondering.
Oh, yes of course!
We have prepared the ultimate
feast in honor of your arrival.
If you can be patient.
Yes, of course. No problem.
Take your time.
You've got to admit it. Those
guys got us pretty good though,
eh fellas?
[Hakkai] I never would have
thought we were worth
impersonating.
Hey, Sanzo, I'm hungry.
How would you like to eat dirt?
All right, knock it off!
Hey, buddy, I don't suppose you
could slip me something to
eat here.
You know you make a lot of
demands for a criminal. Shut up!
I promise I'll be quiet just as
soon as you bring me something
to eat.
What do you think this is?
A hotel? I wouldn't feed
you if I had any food!
Okay. In that case, I'll just
get it myself.
Now that I'd like to see.
Do you have any idea who you're
messing with?
[Goku] Food... Food!
[Guard screams]
Nah-ah-ah-ah. Not so fast.
Honestly how do you expect to
keep an eye on us if you're
running off like that?
[Guard continues screaming]
[Gojyo] Let's see now.
[screams]
[Gojyo] Guard! Does this look
empty to you?
[Guard] Coming, sir!
The sake's not bad.
Where's my beer?
Right here, Sir!
Hey, what is this?
As you can see, a vegetarian
meal fit for a king.
It looks like it's more fit
for rabbits.
What is this? I've had hors
dourves that are more
filling than this.
[Chief] Our village is renown
for its vegetarian cuisine,
and what you have before you is
the finest we have to offer.
Oh, oh my. How very kind of you.
Oh my god! I'm already hungry
again! I thought they'd never
let me stop lecturing.
I've never made up so much
philosophy in my life!
Well we wouldn't eat at all if
we didn't have that famous guy
to imitate.
Consider yourself lucky.
Oh boy, ain't that the truth.
[Fake Hakkai] Could you believe
the nerve of those other guys?
I know! Who were they trying
to fool?
Oh boy! No kidding!
Those were the worst imposters
I've ever seen.
Absolutely no grace or dignity.
By the way, has it every occured
to you guys that this might be
the real Sanzo party?
No way!
It never occured to me either!
[All laugh]
[Fake Sanzo] I say we
leave soon.
[Fake Hakkai] Yeah I can't eat
another morsel of this
vegetarian crap.
[Fake Goku] You got that right.
[Akatsuki] Not so fast!
[All four] What? Who? Huh?
[Akatsuki] I have a matter of
some importance to discuss
with you.
Wait! That's a demon!
That's not possible!
Oh it's very possible.
[Hakkai] Heads up.
Looks like we've got another
assassin in our midst,
gentlemen.
[Gojyo] Hey Goku, wake up.
Breakfast already?
It's comeing!
Oh nice, you ordered out
this time.
Oh god not another one!
You know, these guys are looking
a little blue in the face.
Looks like these are the guys
that are after us.
I'm quaking in my boots.
[Gojyo] Wake up!
They sure move awfully fast for
fakes, don't they?
Someone's manipulating our
little impersonators from
somewhere else.
Time for our morning exercise.
Elder! We've got trouble!
What now? Can't you see
I'm busy.
I'm in the middle of chanting
holy scriptures.
So, what's the plan?
They may be being manipulated,
but they're still human beings.
And we should probably go easy
on them.
What? What's the matter?
[Gojyo] Goku, you stand back.
How come?
Because you can't go easy on
anybody, can ya?
This is no time for chitchat,
now is it?
You're all as good as dead
anyways! So get ready to die!
Aw shit!
What is this?
Master Sanzo is fighting
Master Sanzo!
And he's pretty good at it too.
Man, these guys aren't
push overs.
Whoever's controling them must
have an enormus amount of power.
If this drags on the strain will
eventualy destroy their
human hosts.
Damn, then what're we supposed
to do?
What do you think?
Knock them out so he can't
control them anymore.
The bigger they are the harder
they fall.
That everyone?
We got four!
Yep, that was a pretty
good workout.
We'll let Sanzo do the cleaning
up part.
Good grief, that sure didn't
last very long.
Oh well, I didn't care much
which side ended up dead anyway.
[Sanzo] They're all
enemies, right?
Yes, it's so much simpler to
have them killing each other
rather than messing with
them yourself.
What the?!
Sanzo?! How did you find me?!
What are you, a moron?
Someone had to be using their
powers to manipulate them.
All I had to do was follow
the smell.
Very good, Sanzo,
but now, how good are your
other senses?!
Aw, Sanzo's just showing off.
Good luck up there!
You are a moron.
Now you're asking for it!
Sanzo, your life is mine!
By the dawn of day, I use your
light to propel the darkness,
the sun rises, the night falls
holy scripture...
Send him back!
Hey look!
It is the true savior!
Exactly as the legend describes.
It's him! It's really him!
[Elder] Yes, there can be no
doubt, it is Sanzo!
Every inch of my body feels like
it's burning.
I feel like hell.
Oh god does my head hurt.
How do you like fighting real
demons, you fake bastards?
Boy, you guys got a long way to
go to be like us.
Being a member of the
Sanzo party can get a
little dangerous,
so I would advise finding
other work.
[Sanzo] Well fellas.
W-What is it, sir?
Dress up day is over, now get
the hell out of here.
[Both] Yes, Sir!
[Fake Goku] Wait for me!
[Fake Hakkai] Don't leave me!
Yet again, Master Sanzo has
saved our village from the
demon threat.
It's not like we went out of
our way to save you guys.
To be honest, we only fought
them for our own personal
reasons.
Still you are worthy of
our admiration.
You must have worked quite hard
to develope those abilities we
all witnessed here.
Are you kidding?
I hate hard work more than
anything in the world.
I will never forget this.
Those bastards sure made fools
out of us!
Hey who the hell are you guys?
I was just about to ask you the
same thing.
Don't you recognize the great
Master Sanzo when you
see him?
You should show some respect you
stupid, jerk!
Surely you've heard of us.
Our powers are the stuff
of legends.
Really? YOU'RE the Sanzo Party?
Well that didn't take long,
let's go.
[Fake Goku] Let's not dress like
this anymore.
[Fake Sanzo] I agree...
[Fake Goku] Nothing good
ever happens to us.
[Fake Gojyo] No kidding.
[Goku] A mysterious mechanical
doll suddenly appears out of
nowhere and fires a beam that
wounds Gojyo
Now, something's moving inside
his body! What the hell is that
thing, anyway?
Wait, Sanzo, what are youdoing?
But if you do that, what'll
happen to Gojyo?
Find out next time in
"The Laughing Grim Reaper,"
on Saiyuki.
Don't miss it!