[Narrator] It was a time
when Heaven and Earth
coexsisted peacefully.
Where demon and man were
more than neighbors.
They were brothers.
Here civilization and faith
were born, the foundations
of man.
It was Shangri-La.
But then, the brotherhood of man
and demon turned.
Man became Abel to demon's Cain.
They grew angry, and powerful
and hungry.
And they convened far to the
west under the command of one.
[Monk 1] How dare you! Get down!
[Monk 2] This tree does not bear
fruit for one such as you.
[Goku] Relax! This bush
is loaded.
There's plenty to go around, and
I'm starvin'!
What is it now? What's he done
this time?
Your companion feels entitled
to partake in some of the
local produce.
These peaches are offerings to
the Merciful Goddess! Get him
down now!
A peach is a peach, is a peach.
Get over it!
He's not mcompanion!
It's guilt by association and
that's all!
If you say...
Get down, Goku!
[Sanzo] Dinner's over, let's go.
Go where?
You gonna take me to a real
restaurant?
Huh? are you? Huh? Huh? Hey!
Huh? Huh? Hey! Huh? Huh? Hey!
Shut up!
Ow! What the did you do
that for?!
[Sanzo] Just shut up and get
changed or I'll do it again!
And if you don't move it now,
I'm leaving you behind!
Alright, fine. I'm going.
He is no better than an
unruly child.
Why would a priest with a
spiritual heritage so
respectable as Sanzo travel with
such a frivilous degenerate?
For this I have no answer.
Don't act like I'm not here.
Besides, what I pick up or I
throw away is none of
your business.
Pick up? What do you mean, like
a disease?
Shut your mouth and move
your ass!
Why did I pick him up?
That's what I'd like to know.
[Sanzo] You, are you the one
who's been calling to me?
[Goku] Huh? No, I haven't been
calling to anyone at all.
Wh-Who are you?
Look kid, don't lie to me.
I've heard you calling out to
me for years.
It's annoying, and I'm heard
now so you can quit calling.
Come on. You're coming with me,
it's fate.
[Goku] Wait up!
Hey, come on man, tell me where
we're going! Come on! Tell me!
Hey? Hey, hey? Come on tell me!
Come on, Tell me!
Sanzo, tell me where, man!
Huh? Huh? Huh?
One more sound and I'm going to
kill you!
[Goku] Come on, at least tell me
where we're going!
I promise I'll keep it a secret.
We're going to look for Hakkai
and Gojyo.
We find them and go.
Go where?
[Woman 1] Good luck, Gojyo!
[Woman 2] Come on, you can
do it.
[Soushi] Don't bet on it.
Two pairs, two pairs jacks
over kings.
Wow what a coincidence, I've got
two pairs too.
A pair of queens and another
pair of queens.
I believe the term is four of
a kind.
[Woman 1] Oh, nice!
[Woman 2] Very nice.
Damn it! Just take it all!
[Soushi] Take all of it!
Sorry about that, Soushi.
Believe me, these three queens
around me,
are more important than the four
on the table.
Stop it!
He's lost it. What going on?
I said knock it off!
Step down, Soushi.
It was just a friendly little
game of cards.
Alright then. You can have it
your way.
That sucks. I always made money
off of that guy too.
God, I need a katana to see
through this shit.
Hakuryu, hit the fog lights,
will you?
Holy shit!
Look out kid! Get out of the
way! Hakuryu, transform!
Geeze kid, that was too close.
Are you alright, kid?
You're just a little shaken up.
Come on kid, let's get up and
I'll help you find your
parents. Okay?
My name's Hakkai. Who are you?
Oh? Come on kid, don't be afraid
I'm not gonna hurt you,
I promise.
Don't do that. We're
practically family.
That's right man, I'm just
like you.
Well, maybe I've got a little
more self control.
But what happened? Where are
your power limiters?
[Hakkai] Don't worry, I'll help
you find them.
That settles that.
This kid didn't lose his power
limiter he took the damn
thing off
and he doesn't want it back.
It's time to go!
Whoa! And here I was worried
that you'd be out here all
alone and defencless.
Come on Hakuryu, let's just
leave these boys alone.
They're not going to need
my protection.
Yeah I know, I felt it too.
Dark and hungry.
There's some serious spiritual
shit going down.
Do you can drive a little faster
if you want.
[Goku] Man, I'm hungry!
Come on Sanzo, how long until we
get there, man?
I'm sick of walking and I'm
getting tired of waiting
for lunch!
Hey! I'm talking to you!
And I'm sick of it!
We'll never get there if you
keep taking breaks ever
five minutes!
Why the hell are you being such
a hardass? I'm hungry!
You're a preist, how about a
little compassion!
Look, you and I both know it
isn't possible for you to
starve to death.
Yeah, well you don't know that
for a fact.
Yes I do.
Well instead of turning this
into a death march,
you could've just had Hakkai
pick us up in the jeep!
Shut up and get up!
And what you're sudden buring
desire to go hook up with Hakkai
and Gojyo anyway?
Yeah, I thought that'd getcha.
There's something I need
to confirm.
What do you mean? What do you
need to confirm?
Yesterday, I was summoned to the
Temple of the Setting Sun
in Chang'an.
[Sanzo] Servant of the Northern
God of Heaven, Genjo Sanzo,
humbly presents himself.
[Sanbutsushin 1] It was good of
you to come, Genjo Sanzo.
Sire...
[Sanbutsushin 1] Time is of
the essence.
Pardon us for pressing you.
Of course.
Surely you can sense it, the
dark disturbance that gnaws
at this world.
From the west to east, the
affliction now spans all
of Shangri-La.
[Sanbutsushin 3] The day of
brotherhood is fading.
Demons who once walked in peace
with man grow now savage.
Yes, I have seen it.
[Sanzo] Humans now cower
before demons,
they live their days in terror.
Shangri-La is but a name or
memory. Now it is the very
picture of Hell.
Tell me, do you know what
has caused this abomination?
Have you ever heard whispers
of Gyumaoh?
Gyumaoh!
Tell us, what do you know of
this Gyumaoh?
Gyumaoh...
They say he is the great demon
who refused to coexist with
humans and devoured them.
He devoured them as was
his pleasure.
[Sanbutsushin] Go on.
But Gyumaoh was put to rest in
the Houtou Castle
by the war god, they say that
the Crown Prince Nataku,
defeated the demon in the land
of India far west of here,
more than 500 years ago.
[Sanbutsushin 1] But now,
Gyumaoh may breath again.
He is being revived by someone.
If unopposed this person
will succeed.
Using science from another time
and forbidden magic.
That sounds bad.
Real bad.
No one can predict what will
happen, Goku.
[Sanbutsushi 3] Science and
black magic are diometrically
opposed to one another.
As forbidden as the joining with
humans the negative aura will
destroy a delicate balance.
That which must always maintain
separation can never be
brought together.
And it is this spiritual
imbalance that is causing
the savagery of the
demons unto humankind.
[Sanbutsushin 1] Yes.
And that is why we are forced
to make this demand of you.
You have those with whom you
share a past, Goku, Gojyo,
and Hakkai.
You four must travel India in
the far west, to the root of
this evil!
[Sanbutsushin 2] Discover who is
conducting these experiments to
revive Gyumaoh and why.
You cannot allow the monster to
be resurrected!
So the demons can be recalled
to themselves.
Then Shangri-La can once again
be restored to a land of peace
and tranquility.
As you wish.
So, we hook it to this India
place, where ever that is,
find out who's messing with
magic, make sure this Gyumaoh
guy stays dead,
you look good for the three
heads and the demons go back
to being our buddies! Right?
Let's do it!
It's not as easy as all that.
You worry too much.
It'll be a piece of cake,
Sanzo. Relax!
[Sanzo] You don't get it.
Sounds like a done deal to me.
What do you need Hakkai and
Gojyo for?
[Sanzo] Because, monkey boy, we-
[Rustling in the bushes]
Oh shit!
Watch your back.
Freeze!
Ha! Do you honestly believe a
puny little pistol
will have any effect on a demom
such as I?
Actually, no I don't.
But this isn't just a puny
little pistol.
It's a banishing gun.
Ever heard of it?
Thought so.
No! No, wait!
You know they never listen.
Why don't they ever just
listen to me?
[Goku] Uh Sanzo!
So all these guys are friends
of Gyumaoh?
Took off their power limiters
and switched to the other side.
I smell...
...human.
I'm hungry.
There are too many of them.
This journey's not startin' out
too good.
[Gojyo] So, things are bad
all over.
You know, it looks to me like
Shangri-La's going to hell
in a handbasket.
But I'm betting you guys have a
good idea how to get it back.
It's Gojyo! And look Hakkai!
Long time no see, Goku.
Nice to see you both, even you,
you stupid monkey.
Listen, water wimp, why don't
you watch your mouth, huh?
Hey! You wanna start something?
Come on!
[Goku] Oh pee-yuu, your breath
smells like ass!
[Goku and Gojyo continue
arguing]
Oh boy.
[Goku and Gojyo continue
arguing]
[Sanzo] How did you find us?
[Hakkai] The demonic aura is
strong, I followed its
scent here.
Unfortunatly, Gojyo and I have
witnessed scences like what
you've just experienced.
Gojyo, Goku, and I are the only
demons who seem in control.
Die! All of you, die!
Kinda sad. Had all the attitude
in the world.
But not a goddamn clue how to
use it.
[Demon] Get him!
[Hakkai] Hakuryu, gimme a
second will you?
[Demon] The easy one!
Man that was great, but what the
hell was that?
Actually that was the first
time I used it.
I wasn't sure I could pull
it off.
Okay, I kinda copied a move from
someone else.
So you basically stole it
from someone.
He has ear cuffs and the other
wears a band!
They limit their powers
by choice!
[Demon] You are demons,
are you not?!
And if we are?
You are our kind! Why do you
fight against us?!
[Goku] Good question.
My Lords, I have one question I
wish to ask, if I may.
Why have you appointed these
three to be my companions?
They are demons.
They are demons this is true,
but they are also human.
This is why they can maintain
their sense of self and not
give in to the darker aura.
[Sanbutsushin 2] You have lived
long, Genjo Sanzo, so you should
know this well.
Ironic yes, that the scars each
of them bears from their pasts
are what form the web that
connects you all.
[Goku] We're against you, cause
we're not like you!
[Hakkai] Not technically!
[Gojyo] Like you can talk!
[Sanbutsushin 1] They have a
power and a spiritual strength.
They are the trump cards in your
hand. Remember this.
It is true that I cannot deny
their unique abilities.
But nor can I forget that
demonic blood that flows
within their veins,
My lord, can we truly devine
that this blood could never
gain supremacy, over
their souls?
To place our faith blindly in
a lot such as this would be
foolish, perhaps fatal
[Sanbutsushin 2] Your concern
has been noted. Still, this
does not change what is true.
They are to be your companions.
And it was not the Sanbutsushin
who has appointed these demons
to be your missionaries.
The Merciful Goddess of the
Heavens has decreed it to you.
The Merciful Goddess?!
With all due respect,
I must confess,
the only one I can trust in this
world is myself.
Ever since I lost what was
dearest to me, my heart has
believed this.
That cannot change.
Things can appear differently
if you look with the eyes of
your heart, Genjo Sanzo.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
[Sanbutsushin] Go and meet them
and perhaps you will see for
yourself.
Confirm that what you believe
now is actually true. And look
with different eyes.
What's done...
...is done!
Confrim what is true...
Traitors you would take the
side of the powerless and
arrogant humans!
That is not where you belong!
Do not betray your own kind!
Join us and raise your
voices with ours!
Long live the demon kingdom
of Gyumaoh!
[Gojyo] What a load of crap.
Taking sides with the humans?
Ha! From when I was born, til
the day I die,
the only side I'm on, is mine.
The eye of the heart.
Goku?
Gojyo?
Yeah?
Hakkai?
Yes...
We go... there!
To the west.
[Goku] Well that didn't take
long, just a couple of days
into our trip
and they're already sending
assassins after us. I hate
this job.
Oh yeah, and this bunch of
freaks is led by some nasty
spider skank. Not pretty.
Then, of course, there's the
usual dilemma about dinner.
Look at him - I hate that dude!
[Gojyo] Ah bite me.
[Goku] You wish!
[Goku] Stay tuned for the
next episode!