[Monkeys screech]
[Demon yells]
Man! They're tough!
They're a hell of a lot
more than I bargained for!
[Demon yells]
What, are you blind?
Do we look like ducks?
Maybe one of us looks
like a monkey, but...
At least I'm no water sprite!
This wasn't the deal.
[Hakkai] I apologize.
I'm not usually this prone
to random acts of violence.
But I'm afraid you caught
me on a really bad day.
[Demon] A banishing gun!
Why you're no...
no ordinary monk!
They... they lied to us!
[One lone gunshot]
[Demon yells]
[Sanzo] A trick?
[Goku] They hardly
seemed worth the trouble.
When it's that easy
to kick their ass,
that's when I start to worry.
They didn't really seem like
assassins, that's for sure.
Could be some bandits
got a little more than
they bargained for.
Whoa, you guys smell something?
[Sanzo] Hm?
Hey! Look guys! I found it!
[Goku] Hey! I got it first,
you purple haired pansy!
[Gojyo] Why this is... grade A,
[Gojyo] homebrewed...
WIIIIIIINE!
[Goku] "The Broken Promise".
My sweet, sweet baby!
Who do you think would ferment
wine in an old tree like that?
[Hakkai chuckles]
A monkey, that's who.
Not you too, Hakkai!
What'd I do to you?
Duuumbass. The monkey he's
referring to isn't you, dork.
He meant monkeys, real monkeys
made the wine, not you.
Oh please.
[Hakkai] Monkeys sometimes
gather fruits into tree hollows,
that then ferment to make wine.
They call it monkey wine,
I believe.
Wow, that's so weird.
[Gojyo chuckles]
[Gojyo] So you see, real
monkeys are so much smarter.
I don't recall you ever
making wine, so what
does that make you?
[Gojyo] My talents come
later on in the process.
I'm a drinking specialist.
[Goku] What's so special
about up-chucking?
[Sanzo] So now we're
stealing from monkeys.
That's pathetic.
That so?
So, you want some?
You see? It's not so pathetic
to steal from monkeys when
it taste like that, eh?
I'm only drinking what
the bartender gave me,
so technically it's
not like I stole it.
Aye aye aye. You monks aren't
more moral than us, you just
rationalize a lot better.
[Sanzo] Hmph.
[Goku] Hey, Sanzo. Let
me have a sip, will ya?
[Sanzo] No, you're just a kid.
[Goku] Don't be such a hard-ass!
You drank when you were a kid!
Holy temples do not
stock liquor, idiot.
They only keep a supply
of spirits handy.
[Hakkai chuckles]
[Gojyo] That's too good.
What? What are spirits?
Basically, it's just liquor.
Then you WERE drinking,
you big liar!
Shut up. You can call
it whatever you want,
but I'm telling you, I didn't
drink when I was a little kid.
He's lying.
And little brats like you
should not be in a hurry
to start drinking.
[Monks chuckling and having
a good time, loudly]
[All] Kouryuu!
So you're skipping
training to drink?
But, we aren't drinking any
wine. This is spirits.
Calling it something else
won't change what it is.
[Monk] No, wait, Kouryuu!
Won't you have a drink with us?
If you can't even handle
a simple drink, w-well then
you're not strong enough to be
here with us. Isn't that right?
Yes, yes! Don't you want to
be worthy, just like us?
Like Priest Koumyou Sanzo?
[Koumyou] So I'm only
worthy of a drunkard.
[Monks gasp]
[Monks fumbled out "Priest
Sanzo" and "Master Sanzo"]
[Monk 1] I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
[Monk 2] Please forgive us!
Master Sanzo...
[Koumyou] Kouryuu.
Do not be in too much of a
hurry to indulge in drinking.
Drinking is much like
the wine itself.
It can only be enjoyed
once the body and soul
have fully matured.
If your body is young,
my dear, young apprentice,
the wine will eat away at it.
And likewise if the soul
is too young, then the wine
will eat away at that too.
A taste before the proper
age will be bitter.
[Koymyou] Kouryuu...
[Kouryuu] Yes, sir?
[Koumyou] Concentrate on
your studies and you will
become a man soon enough.
And when that happens...
Let us both have
a drink together.
[Sanzo] But before I could
reach adulthood, my master...
[Goku] Sanzo? Sanzo?
I told you not to drink!
Come on! I just want a taste!
Is that right?
[Gojyo] Hey man, what gives?
Well, we'll just see about that.
Bottoms up!
[Goku & Gojyo] Heeey!
Hey Sanzo, I don't suppose you
could please leave some for me.
Well, looks like it's all gone.
It smelled so good too.
Dammit, I was looking foward
to trying some homemade hooch.
Well? What are we waiting for?
We're in town, guys!
You know what that means!
I can get some food!
Oh well. Can't really
argue with that, can I?
And I know I could sure use a
glass of wine with my dinner.
Right? And I think you
should pay for it... Sanzo.
If you say so.
[Goku] C'mon guys!
Stop torturing me!
[Goku] Let's go to town!
[Hakkai] Let's go!
Somehow I doubt they'll
have monkey wine in stock.
[Gojyo] The only reason
you didn't get any is
because the temperance
of our fellow monk here.
[Sanzo] Our teachings
compelled me to do it.
[Gojyo] Is that so?
[Sanzo] I did it for Goku.
[Gojyo] Oh, give it up.
Okay now, are there
any more contestants?
Come on now! Celebrate
our grand opening with us!
All you can drink,
[Goku] Sanzo! Look here!
[Owner] compliments
of the Yamatoya group.
[Goku] Looks like they're
having some kind of contest.
[Owner] You think you
can handle your liquor?
[Owner] Here's your
chance to prove it.
[Hakkai] What is this?
[Owner carries on]
It's a drinking contest
to promote the new tavern
that just opened up in town.
You can't enter unless you've
got a team together.
But if you win, everybody
on the team receives a
year's supply of wine.
That so?
[Sanzo] Don't bother.
Any wine they give you is
bound to be the cheap stuff.
[Fei Youngest] Yeah, yeah. You
just keep telling yourself that.
You three losers couldn't out
drink the famous Fei brothers
even if you tried to.
I believe all I said was
that it's cheap wine.
Don't the little feather weights
always seem to come up with
the lamest excuses.
These guys don't look like
much of a challenge to me.
Are you three hayseeds actually
trying to pick a fight with us?
I'm sorry! Forgive me.
Perhaps I wasn't obvious
enough, so let me be clearer.
Not a single one of you
three panty-waisted pussies
could handle a shot
glass of weak lemonade.
A sissy who dyes his hair pink.
Some dandy who uses a monocle?
And Goldielocks, the
effeminate monk in a dress.
[Fei Eldest laughs]
You gotta be kidding me.
You three girls... might
want to stick with soda pop.
Heh, sure is pretty.
Oh yeah?
Hm? Would you like to sign up?
Yeah, but... Well, uh.
I was simply wondering if
it would be possible if
we could use your best
wine for the contest.
[Owner] You must be joking!
I'd go broke if I did that!
Just put it on my tab.
[Owner] What?!
[Fei Eldest] Whoo! Lucky for us!
[Sanzo] But if I win,
it's on the Fei brothers.
Is this actually for real?
We can't afford to
pay for all that.
What? What happened? Did I
miss something? Fill me in!
Why thank you! Winning
will be twice as sweet
knowing you paid for it.
Why don't you save it till
you've actually won?
Oh boy. Sanzo. Look Hakuryu,
his eyes are already dilated.
And he hasn't had
a drop to drink.
[Owner] Alright!
Attention please!
Everyone get ready! The drinking
contest is about to begin!
Sanzo! Gojyo! Hakkai!
Good luck you guys!
The contest rules are simple.
Drink as much as possible,
and the last team with
someone left standing wins!
Ready... set... begin!
[Crowd cheers wildly]
[Li] Wow, monk, you're
really knocking them back!
So, did you learn to drink like
that in your little seminary?
Tell me where to sign up!
[Current opposing team laughs]
Heeey, you know, my temple's
filled with a bunch of
old fuddy-duddies.
Not like you guys. HURK!
[Sanzo] Pitiful...
That's too funny.
And I haven't even
gotten started yet.
These guys are pathetic.
I hope the others last until
I get a good buzz going.
I need to get smashed.
[Sanzo] We're in good shape.
But we've still got
a long way to go.
And we'll drink plenty by
the time the day's through.
Heh! We'll I'll be damned.
That monk's not half bad.
That's true. But he's not
nearly good enough to beat
the likes of us, man.
You said it!
Sanzo! Gojyo! Hakkai!
Hang in there!
[Owner] Looks like we're down
to the real professionals now!
We'll take a short break while
our staff clears away any
passed out participants!
Full of a bunch of...
old fuddy-duddies...
It looks like... things
have just started to...
get interesting, folks!
We're down to the
fabulous Fei brothers!
And the Traveling Monk's Team!
Who will be the first to pass
out? Let's find out, shall we?
[Crowd cheers wildly]
Sanzo! Gojyo! Hakkai!
Show 'em who's boss!
I wish that stupid monkey
would just shut the hell up.
[Gojyo] Hoo-ee, he's giving
me a pounding headache.
Hey! C'mon! Bring on the booze!
[Gojyo] Huh?
Come to think of it,
I've never actually
seen Hakkai drunk before.
[Sanzo] We might have
underestimated him.
What's wrong? Your
hand looks shaky.
Ha! Not at all.
Why does your face
look so red then?
Whatever. I noticed you guys
were swaying a little bit.
Your vision's already blurry.
[Crowd cheers]
Hehe. What's wrong, Goldielocks?
You look woozy.
That all you got?
I didn't hurt yer feelins,
did I, pretty boy?
[Hakkai] Sanzo?
You dumb bastard.
You actually have the
gall to mock me, do you?
Maten-!
PLEASE!
Don't you think unleashing a
scripture that controls Heaven
and Earth is a little severe?
[Sanzo] Hakkai.
[Hakkai] Yeah?
It's all up to you now.
[Hakkai] Sanzo!
[Glass falls over]
[Hakkai] Huh?
[Gojyo snores softly]
Well then, it looks like
it's up to me and...
[Snores]
[Hakkai] Look at that.
Listen! We have
ourselves a champion!
The traveling monk's team wins!
[Crowd cheers]
Wow, they did it!
Hakkai! Way to go!
I... did...
Okay.
[Owner] Hahahaha! I gotta
hand it to you, you sure
can hold your liquor.
Drink up!
Yes, well, maybe just one
more drink, if you insist.
Though, I should probably find
a place for them to sleep.
Oh, well. If that's all you
four gentlemen are looking
for, than look no further!
You're more than welcome
to stay here tonight.
Are you sure? Why thank you!
Then just one more.
[Owner chuckles]
[Owner] You get to die, passed
out, drunk on good wine.
More than you jerks deserve.
What the-?
Wha-what is this?!
You cheap bastard.
Attacking us while
we're passed out, huh?
I bet chicks hate you.
[Hakkai] Not very hospitable.
[Gojyo] Hey, wake up. Your
family's here to see you.
Cut that out.
What the hell's going on here?!
You knew I wanted you dead?
How did you know?
Moron, your wine
was way too good.
Some of the liquor you served
us, was the exact same monkey
wine we found in the forest
on our way into town.
That was what tipped us off.
I had hoped that would
slip by all of you.
We are connoisseurs.
And I willing to place
a bet that you sent
those demons as well.
I'm not terribly impressed.
Damn it.
You can call me Shin!
Shin Taijin!
The one who will
kill all of you!
Attack!
Hey! You have monkeys do
your fighting for you?!
Ha! That's all that I require
to take care of a bunch
of worthless drunks!
Uck. I don't care for
your style, old man!
There's not enough room
for us to fight in here!
Let's take this outside!
Something wrong?
Why are you staggering?
Hey, listen monkeys!
I'm about to teach you
degenerate primates the
true meaning of the
little phrase for...
"Let's take it outside"!
Dammit to hell! These monkeys
sure are a pain in the ass!
I resent that!
You resemble that.
Goku, remember those monkeys
are being manipulated.
Please go easy on them.
Roger!
You guys really annoy me!
They really are drunk!
What's going outside... what's
that suppose to accomplish?
Huh?
Impossible!
Sorry we're late.
How... could you...
kill them all?!
We didn't.
If there's one thing we know,
it's how to handle a monky.
I'm no monkey!
Handle this!
Learn to heel!
[Monkeys squeak]
How cute!
Hey you guys, look at the-
Hey! Guys, get 'em off me!
[Gojyo] Aw, look. Back
with his own kind.
[Goku] Get 'em off me! Guys!
That was a pretty
mean trick you played.
Acting all drunk like that.
No act...
I'm completely plastered.
But there's a very wise saying
I heard a long time ago.
[Koumyou] Kouryuu, there's an
old saying that's been passed
down from generation
to generation.
It goes something like this.
"Consume wine...
[Koumyou & Sanzo] don't let
the wine consume you."
Oooh my. How can they sleep in
the middle of a bar like that?
Hey, Sanzo.
What can you do?
[Koumyou] Kouryuu!
Kouryuu!
[Kouryuu] Master...
Shall we share a drink?
Really? But I'm just...
[Sanzo] Aaaaah. Wine
never tasted so good.