[Yaone] Sanzo and the betrayers
travel north by northwest, seven
kilometers from our location.
[Dokugakauj] They rode in on a
dragon that turns into a jeep.
They make shit time. We can head
'em off, no problem.
[Kougaji] And what of
Mother's orders?
[Doku] Send in more assassins,
of course.
Bad idea if you ask me.
[Kougaji] Of course it's a
bad idea!
I'm sick of losing
my brothers!
She throws warriors at them as
if they were sticks for a fire!
[Doku] Relax. That's why we're
having this discussion, hothead.
[Lirin] I'm over this already!
Why are we talking about this?!
Let's just go and take care of
them ourselves!
She's right. If I want to save
Mother I have to fight myself.
It's just...
[Doku] Kou, Lirin's right.
We can take them down.
Or are you feeling a little
nervous about this bitch and
her little demonic revival?
I'm just fine! I know what needs
to happen here.
[Yaone] My Lord...
You have something to say?
Why don't you allow me to go
and kill them?
[Yaone] I have an idea.
[Kougaiji] No, it's
too dangerous.
[Yaone] You're being stubborn.
Let me do this. Think of it as a
pay back for the time you were
there for me.
[Kougaiji] I said no.
[Yaone] Then look at it
this way, I am your own
personal apothecary.
I've got a way with powders and
powers. I can use them to
heal... or to kill.
Okay. You win.
No way! So you'll let me?
Hold it! I don't want you to go
yet, you need to listen to
me, Yaone.
I know they look like the
biggest bunch of dumbasses,
but they're very powerful.
Don't take any risks.
I won't. I've got a plan.
I know where they are. They've
got to stop and eat sometime.
I'll set up at a tavern, get a
job and wait.
And when they show up I'll
suggest the blue plate,
and they'll never know just what
ingredient makes it special
until it's too late.
Miss, another plate of
xiaolongbao, please!
Another beer when you get a
minute, honey!
Yaone, don't forget table 20 and
that pork chop!
Me and my bright ideas.
Hey! That is not on the menu!
Oh, come on! Look, I'm a really
big tipper.
OW!
What the hell did you do
that for?!
Who did it?! Did you see?
Who did it?
Who threw the damn ashtray?!
There they are!
Okay miss, we're all ready to
order now.
Yeah, I'll be right there!
[Goku] Gimme the sweet-and-
sour pork,
[Gojyo] A bottle of import,
[Goku] liver and scallions,
and the
[Gojyo] uh, some crab cakes,
[Goku] prawns in chili sauce,
[Gojyo] fried noodles
[Goku] Let's see what else?
[Sanzo] Will you shut up?!
Great! But can I reccomend the
blue plate special?
[Gojyo] Sure, we'll have one
of those and an ashtray.
They're the ones who threw
the ashtray?
Hmph, the one they save is the
one to slay them.
How ironic.
[Sanzo] So, what do you think?
[Gojyo] About what? What are you
talking about?
[Sanzo] It's been over a month
since we left Chang'an.
Iced as many demons as there are
stars in the sky,
and almost all of them assassins
sent by Gyumaoh's number one
son Kougaiji.
You know demons, there about as
fond of taking orders as Goku's
fond of you.
Yet, the demons seem willing
to follow Kougaiji to their
own graves.
[Gojyo] Just don't get sloppy
or distracted.
They'll keep coming all the way
till we get there.
[Hakkai] I'm not so concerned
about why they follow Kougaiji.
What I want to know is who
Kougaiji's taking orders from.
[Yaone] Here it is!
You're gonna love it! It's to
die for.
Yeah!
It looks like this is the whole
menu. You think we ordered
enough food?
For Goku I wouldn't bet on it.
[Goku] Let's eat! I'm starvin'
to death!
Well, you've got the death
part right.
Alright everybody, dig in!
[Tray hits the floor]
[Yaone][startled yelp]
You're right man, I think the
service could be much
better here.
Stop! Let go! I've got tables to
wait on!
I could kill him in a second.
God, I hate undercover work!
Ow! Ow! Ah!
You don't like the service here?
Maybe you should order some
thing else.
[Bandana] Buddy, you better let
him go, nice and easy.
Shut up, or I'm gonna nail
you with another ashtray.
Right here, bang.
You did it?! Well it's about
time you came clean!
Oh, thanks a lot, jerk.
[Goku cries dramaticly]
You! What kind of monster
are you?!
I believe I feel a food fight
coming on.
Loser picks up the check.
Bring it on, litte brat! I'll
kick your ass!
Oh yeah?!
Yeah! Get 'em!
[Fighting sounds]
I find it mildly disconcerting
that they're fighting the very
same people we're supposed to
be protecting.
I'm not getting stuck with the
check again.
You're friends of theirs aren't
you? Get up and fight like
a man!
Face flat on the floor.
I think these boys have had
quite enough to drink.
Don't you?
[Both drunks] We're just getting
this party started.
So let's do this.
[Fighting continues]
[Owner] Stop it! Gentlemen!
Please, stop it!
[Fighting continues]
Kougaiji said not to trust
them, that they're the enemy.
He said not to take any risks.
Is this some kind of trick?
It's just that... they're
different. Different than
I thought they'd be.
[Hakkai] I'm sorry about
all this.
I know sometimes our methods can
be extreme.
[Yaone] It's not that.
We're just trying to save a
pretty lady from an ugly thing.
[Kougaiji] You there. Stop.
What are you doing?
[Servant] Your Highness!
Apparently she is daughter
of a medicine merchant,
because of her beauty, she is to
be presented to Hyakugan Maoh.
Well there's a change in plan,
she's mine now.
Come with me.
But... Y-Your Highness...
[Kougaiji] Maoh has this little
habbit of treating beautiful
women like playthings,
then eats them when he becomes
bored with them.
Don't get me wrong now.
I didn't save you for any
romantic notions.
But from here on out you're
working for me.
As an apothecary, of course.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
And he kept is his word.
He never asked anything
more of me.
Why do I feel so hesitant?
Is this how I repay him for
his kindness? With betrayl?
These men are the enemy and
Kougaiji's enemies are
my enemies.
Wow. So you want some more?
Okay then, come on.
You asshole! You won't be nearly
as cocky when my friends and I
get through with you.
Damn, my eyes are on fire.
Something's happening.
I can't breathe.
Smells like medicine.
Cover your mouth, don't
breathe in!
Gojyo! Aw no you don't, man.
Wake up!
[Hakkai] Sanzo! Goku!
Still breathing. He's not dead.
[Yaone] No, he's not. It's just
sleeping powder.
We don't want to be dragging
outsiders into our private
affair. I'm sure you agree.
You did this? It was you!
And you, you shouldn't have held
your breath.
You know, I really was hoping
you were going to sleep
through this.
But... oh well.
Her bracelet, it's a
power limiter.
You're an assassin. You're a
demon sent by Kougaiji!
You must be the smart one of
the group.
My name's Yaone. I kinda figured
you might want to know my name.
Because I'm going to kill
you, traitor.
You're going to wish you'd
fallen asleep.
[Hakkai] Why are you doing this?
[Yaone] I was wrong.
You're not the smart one.
En garde!
Hey! Take it easy!
Stand still!
Just die!
Stop. You don't want to kill me.
Maybe she does!
Shit. He's got powers.
Will you please stop this?
Huh?
Sanzo! Get up! Gojyo!
Oh man...
Where's Hakkai? Why's Hakkai
not here?
Well, because he's...
Because he's outside fighting
the waitress.
[Yaone] Why won't you just die?
Aw shit!
I want you to know that you're
the one who forced it to turn
out this way.
When I blow up that tavern all
that blood is going to be on
your hands.
I'm sorry about this,
I really am.
Eeeh, that would be my doing.
My bad. I just saw this bomb
lying around and just defused
so no one got hurt.
I've lost. Kougaiji is going to
kill me.
And he should. I'm not worthy to
serve him. I'm a detrament to
the cause.
[Hakkai] I'm sorry. I mean that,
I'm really sorry.
I wish none of this had
to happen.
[Yaone] Don't touch me!
I thought you were hurt.
[Yaone] God don't make it worse,
don't help me. Kill me.
He will.
And he has every right to do so.
I'm worthless!
Wait!
[Yaone] Get back!
I'm sorry, Kougaiji,
I wasn't able to repay you.
I'm so sorry.
Hey! What are you doing?!
[Kanan] Gonou...
Gonou, listen to me.
How can I let this child be
born? You know what a monster
his father is.
[Hakkai] Kanan...
Goodbye, Gonou. Goodbye.
Kougaiji, I'm so sorry.
STOP!
You... You saved me...
[Sanzo] That's him... Kougaiji!
So this is the Sanzo party?
Not impressed.
Me neither.
[Kougaiji] I've come to retrieve
my associate.
That's all.
I have a feeling we'll be seeing
eachother again.
I suggest you try staying alive
until then, if you can.
Don't go. Stick around awhile.
Goku! No!
Stop it. It's embarassing.
[mocking] "Stop it." I hate
this guy.
And before you try anything...
That's enough.
[Kougaiji] How nice of you to
come up here and join us.
[Sanzo] Yeah well I'm all
about service.
You know what's pressing against
the back of your head right?
Yeah, I know what it is, priest.
I've got a lot of questions for
you, Your Highness.
I'll bet you do, and believe me
I got all your answers.
But if you want 'em, you're
gonna have to take them and
that could make things messy.
[Kougaiji] You know, you've all
been pretty luck so far.
But you and your little friends
might want to ask yourselves
a question,
namly how long you think that
luck is going to last.
Look, hair-do, I'm in a bad mood
so if you could just cut to the
chase, I'd appreciate it.
Let the chase begin.
Goddamnit!
I should have just shot him.
Are you all right, Goku?
[Goku] He's powerful!
He's super powerful! Oh shit,
this kicks ass!
He's smiling...
Looks like monkey boy's happy
to finally have met our
little playmate.
Now we have a face to match
the name.
Yep. I can't wait to see that
face again and wipe that smirk
right off.
Let's hope our next little
meeting provides more
information.
Well, I think we found out what
we need to know now.
It's no wonder the demons follow
him he's incredibly powerful,
and he'll risk his life to save
one of his own.
[Kougaiji] Are you hurt?
[Yaone] No, I am all right.
I'm so very sorry, my lord!
I failed you.
This was my idea and I failed,
and now they know who you are.
I'm a weakling. I don't know
why you save me, you should
have just-
[Kougaiji] Shut up!
When I enlisted you in my
service I don't recall you being
stupid enough to throw you
life away!
You promised me you'd follow me
to the ends of the Earth.
Are you going to keep your word
or not?
Of course. I will follow you
forever, to the ends of
the Earth.
Till the day I die.
[Sanzo] It's cold tonight.
A little. It is a little.
[Hakkai] It was cold the night I
met you, three years ago.
Three years? I can't believe
it's only been three.
No offence, but it feels like
it's been a hell of a lot
longer than that.
[Hakkai chuckles]
None taken.
A lot of shit's happened that
makes the years seem longer.
And to be honest there's a lot
of shit I'd just as soon forget.
Hakkai, if you feel you have
to go take care of some
unfinished business,
I want you to go do what you
have to do and don't look back.
I mean that.
You don't have to go with us.
You follow your own path.
Just make sure revenge is a
path you want to take.
I want to be here. I have no
idea where this road is going,
but I know that I'm meant to be
on it.
You know?
[Door slams open]
Sanzo, grab your shit! We're
changing rooms!
Him! He drew picture on my feet
while I was sleeping!
I couldn't sleep with your
snoring. What else was I
suppose to do?
[Goku] Don't ever touch my feet!
No, don't touch any part of me!
[Gojyo] Touch you? Dude, I don't
wanna be in the same room
with you!
[Goku] You're no dream date
either, Violet.
[Gojyo] I could maybe put up
with the snoring but you fart
in your sleep too.
[Sanzo] That's it!
That's enough!
[Goku] That's a lie!
I'm not changing rooms with
anyone, so shut up!
And if you don't shut up,
I'll shut you up!
[Both] [mocking] Oh no! We're
so scared!
[Hakkai] OK, I'll stay, but I
want you to know that
[Goku] What's that smell?!
Gross! You stink!
[Hakkai] I reserve the right to
walk at any time I deem fit.
[Goku] Why don't you ever take
a bath?!
[Gojyo] I take baths!
[Goku] No you don't! I've never
seen you!
[Sanzo] Just take me with you.
[Goku] Bet I know why!
[Gojyo] No you don't!
[Goku] Oh yes I do! You're a
water sprite,
and you're afriad of the water!
You can't even swim!
[Gojyo] Shut up!
[Goku] Oh that's so lame,
you suck!
[Goku] Really dude,
you just suck!
[Gojyo] I'm gonna kick your ass.
[Hakkai] Ladies, ladies please.
[Goku] I'd love to tell you
that as our journey west
continues things get
easier for us.
Not the case, I'm afraid. And
if having to fight pissed off
demons wasn't bad enough,
we find out we might not even be
able to trust our friends.
Although, to be honest, it's
not like we have a lot of those
in the first place.
No matter. Just be sure not
to miss the next adventure
of Saiyuki!