I'm so stuffed!
I never thought I'd live to
hear those words pass
through your lips, Goku.
It's been a while since we
had a proper meal.
Well I'm full. What do we
do now, huh?
We'll find somewhere to stay for
tonight and then we'll head out
first thing in morning.
Then first, we should look for
a hotel.
We're in luck, I believe there's
a very nice one in the back of
this very restaurant.
Well then...
Gojyo, something wrong?
[Gojyo] We don't leave till
tomorrow, we've already picked
an inn.
So there's only one thing left
to do.
Eat a meal.
Fool! Damn moronic monkey!
Can't you ever talk about
anything else?! You're
driving me crazy!
Cruisin'... Cruisin' for chicks.
"Sweet Child of Mine."
[Hakkai] You're just letting
him go?
Yeah sure, why shouldn't I?
Hey, Hakkai, why don't we use
our night off to go shopping?
[Hakkai] That Sounds good.
We've needed to pick up some
more supplies for awhile
now, let's go.
Woohoo!
Hey, I'm running low on
cigarettes, so why don't you
pick up a carton for me?
And just because this a borrowed
ATM card,
doesn't mean you should waste it
on getting food for Goku.
Tightass!
[Gojyo] Let's see if any women
meet my standards.
Classy... But she'd expect a
call in the morning.
No bad, dig the attitude, file
her under maybe.
Oh boy, you will pay for the
privlage of having those jewels
hang around your neck in public.
They'd expect you to pay for
this and that, and then
what happens?
They act all high and mighty
and boss you around.
What the hell is that?!
Do they think they look cute
dressed that way?
They're the type that put
sugar in your gas tank if
you dump them.
I hate that.
I wish I hadn't thought
about that.
Oops, sorry, man.
Hold it right there.
Hey look a fight!
[Man 1] The skinny guy's about
to get his ass kicked. Come on!
[Thug] I can't believe it.
You bumped into me on purpose.
I think you broke my arm.
[Gojyo] Oh man, you've got to be
kidding me.
That's best excuse you can up
with to pick a fight?
Heh. I like you, I just may let
you walk out of here.
With some broken bones, if you
give me all your money.
[Gojyo] Aw come on now, are we
going to do this or what?
Look, stop your blabbing will
ya? I'm sort of in a hurry.
No one... makes fun of me!
Too slow, baldy!
[Gojyo] I've got no time to
waste on educating meat heads.
[Gojyo] What the?
Hello there!
[Gojyo] Look, I'm sure you're
very nice and all but,
you see, I'm just not ready for
that level commitment at the
moment. Okay?
Okay.
[Gojyo] I'm glad we can both be
adults about this.
So long!
Hey, wait a second, Mister!
I have something important to
tell you.
I really like you.
What luck. First I run into
some moron and now I got this
bugar eater chasing after me.
Could it get any worse?
Will you please stop
following me?!
Nuh-uh! I'm going to follow you
around all day until you listen
to what I have to say!
Hey!
Just how am I suppose to
pick up chicks with that
baggage around?
[Meihou] Wait!
Wait!
Wait for me!
[crashing]
[Gojyo] Go away!
[Meihou] Where are you going?
[Gojyo] Away from you?
[Meihou] What are you doing
in there?
[Gojyo] For crying out loud!
[Meihou] I can see you!
[Gojyo] Ah!
[crashing]
[Meihou] Wait! Wait, come back!
[Gojyo running into something]
Come back here!
Looks like I gave her the slip.
Hey there!
Look here, missy...
I'm not a missy. I'm Meihou.
All right, Meihou, I'm going
to try asking you nicely,
like this,
for the love of god, will you
please go and try to find
someone else to play with?
Nuh-uh!
Look, your Big Brother has
some really important business
that he need to attend to
right away. Okay?
What kind of business is it?
I sort of have to find me
a date.
I got an idea. Why don't I go on
a date with you!
Maybe when you're just a little
bit older.
[Goku] That's Gojyo...
Why'd you stop here? What's the
big hold up?
Go-Gojyo's gotten so desperate
he's resorted to picking up
underaged girls!
Gojyo?
Where?
What the?
You're crazy, nobody's there.
I swear I saw him with a girl
about yea big.
And they were walking together
holding hands.
I just don't buy it.
Look, he may not appear it, but
he's normal.
You sure?
Looks good!
Here's the deal. You go home
as soon as you're done with
that, you got it?
Okay, then I won't eat anymore!
Aw come on!
Oh, all right.
Go ahead and eat it, it's okay.
Yay!
[Meihou] Hey, Mister?
You never told me what your
name was.
That so? My name is Gojyo.
Gojyo, I'm Sha Gojyo.
I don't like that name.
[Meihou] Say, Gojyo?
I want to ask you something
important, okay?
Alright, you win.
You'll listen?
I don't think I have much of a
choice, do I?
Here goes...
I would like to hire your
services for a night, okay?
Gojyo, I want to hire you for
the night, okay?
[Gojyo] Do you even know what
that means?
Gojyo, you are strong,
aren't you?
Yeah, I do my best to stay
in shape.
And that's exactly why I'd like
to hire you.
Oh my god.
A guy like me isn't
cheap, honey.
[Meihou] Okay, so I don't
have much,
but I can give you this.
But this is just a worthless
piece of-
Okay, tell me what you want.
[Meihou] Say, Mother?
How long will it be before
we can stop at a town where
there are no demons?
Hush. Don't worry, I'm sure
we'll find a safe place any
day now, baby.
That's right, Meihou. So, let's
get some sleep.
[Strange noises]
[Mom] Don't come out of there,
understand?
I understand.
Don't make any noise.
And in the morning, head into
town and don't look back.
What about you?
[Mom] I love you.
[Meihou] Mother!
[Meihou] I told the townspeople,
but they didn't believe me.
I don't know if it's because
I'm a kid,
or because they're scared of
demons but they wouldn't
listen to me.
I see now, why you were
so persistent.
[Gojyo] Then shall we get going?
You just bought yourself one
demon ass kicker.
[Goku & Hakkai] We're back.
Wow look, Gojyo still hasn't
made it back here yet.
[Hakkai] Forgive us for being
so late.
Goku's nagging me so much I
finally broke down and went
on a bit of a spending spree.
That's okay. It's not my money.
But more importantly, what did
you make of the place?
[Hakkai] Seems peaceful enough,
lively too, but...
But?
[Hakkai] I did hear one rumor.
[Sanzo] What rumor's that?
[Hakkai] It sounds like some
demons have taken residence
in the forest just a little west
of town.
There's been quite a few reports
of some missing relatives.
I'm betting it's the work of our
old friends.
The dissapearences seem
to be occuring with greater
frequency I'm afraid.
Hey! I saw something even
more disturbing!
Gojyo was on a date with an itty
bitty girl this big!
[Sanzo] Get out of here.
I'm not passing judgement,
I'm just saying.
What should we do?
[Sanzo] The forest is
directly in our path.
So we'll find out either way.
Why don't I go out and ask
around a little more?
See what I can find.
[Sanzo] You do that.
[Meihou] This is the place.
The townspeople say this forest
is haunted by spirits,
and no one dares to come
near it.
[Gojyo] Spirits and demons, I
gotta tell ya, they're all the
same to me, honey.
[Meihou] Gojyo...
[Gojyo] So this is where your
family was attacked.
I know you're here.
What?
Just talking to myself.
Come on, let's go.
But where are we going?
Demon hideout.
Are you ready to go take
a look, princess?
Uh, I guess.
[Gojyo] Hello? Anybody home?
[Meihou] It looks abandoned.
Wh-What is it?
Something's not right.
What's not right?
At first glance, it has all the
trappings of an ordinary home,
but I feel like we've
been thrown into a
miniature dollhouse.
And that demonic aura...
It's reverberating through the
entire place so that I can't
locate it.
[Meihou] Gojyo, I'm scared.
[Gojyo] Beyond the door?
What the hell is that?!
Let's go!
[Demonic chuckling]
[Meihou] It's them!
[Gojyo] No!
[Meihou] Let me go!
[Gojyo] Calm down, Meihou!
Check this out! Ah ha!
[Demonic chuckling]
Well, it looks like we're in the
whale's stomach so to speak.
But first we have to find a way
out of here. You with me?
[Meihou screams]
This, I don't need.
Move it!
Get back!
Eat this!
Okay get ready to jump. Now!
Man this thing is persistent!
Look, Gojyo!
[Meihou] he door!
Damn!
Gojyo, hurry!
That's not very likely.
Gojyo!
Stand back!
You'll just get swallowed
up too!
But if you don't leave with me
you're going to die!
You're not going to get rid of
me that easily, Meihou.
[Meihou] No! GOJYO!
Did you hear that?
See? I told you they were
an item!
[Demonic laughter]
[Demon] What good fortune.
I never expected anyone would
willing show up here to
be eaten.
Your hospitality sure leaves
something to be desired
there, buddy.
[Demon] A smartass. I usually
find them difficult to stomach.
I always did have a
sharp tongue.
[Demon] Who are you?
No one.
Fine, sometimes it's better not
to know what you're eating
So, do you mind if I ask
you something?
Do you keep those alive
over there?
I like my food to be
freshly picked.
Well thanks. That's good
to know.
But I'm afraid I'm going to have
to eat you right away.
Ooh, scary. Do tell me,
why is that?
Because I can smell
you're dangerous!
Well, well, that was
perfect timing.
You know, you really add some
color to the place.
Yeah, yeah, just get me down.
I think we should take
photograph.
Anything but that.
Aw don't be shy now.
I'm not finished with you!
You just get back, Goku!
Thank you!
Damn! It's everywhere!
Hakkai, isn't there something
you can do?!
That's real easy for you
to say...
You might want to try aiming
for that?
It kind of looks like
a weakness.
Really? You don't say?
I'm gonna say we bet on
Hakkai's intuition.
I agree. He is a gambler
after all.
Here we go!
Oh, no, you're not!
And now, you're unarmed.
Know what? I always prefer to
pull weeds...
...with my hands
Take that!
It's Mother and- and Father!
[Meihou] Mother!
Meihou!
[Meihou] Gojyo!
[Gojyo] I'm happy for
you, Meihou.
[Meihou] Thank you, Gojyo...
[Gojyo] Yeah well, so long.
Oh, I almost forgot.
this looks better on you anyway.
But Gojyo, I haven't give you
anything as payment, nothing!
I'll look you up in about
ten years.
Until then, they pendant will be
the way that I find you.
I'll sure sweet-talk you good
and proper then.
That's a promise.
Gojyo, I can't wait!
Ten years, huh?
By the way, I don't get it,
how did you three morons ever
figure out where you could
find me, huh?
We wanted to get a look at that
girlfriend of yours.
We kept hearing all these
strange rumors.
Someone fitting your
description had rampaged
through town,
then took off into the woods
with a little girl. What do
you make of that?
That little girl was
pretty cute.
Though I had no idea you had
such peculiar tastes.
Do you wanna die, monkey?!
What? It's the truth, isn't it?
You cradle-robbing water sprite.
That's it!
You're so dead!
[Sanzo] Shut up! Or I'll kill
you both!
[Sanzo] Three companions come
together in the steady rain,
each with their own wounds
to heal.
The pursuer and the pursued.
Then the wheels of fate slowly
began to turn.
Who knows what the future holds
when a man's past comes back to
haunt him.
"The Storm of Fate" Next time
on Saiyuki.