[Sanzo] When the walls
seperating the heavens
and earth fell,
the gods sent four envoys
to bring stability to
certain times.
Myself...
Son Goku...
Sha Gojyo...
Cho Hakkai...
One by one, demons
came to defeat us.
And one by one, they fell.
Even the great Kougaiji
in the end, proved to be no
match for the Sanzo party.
But we had yet to face the
greatest of all assassins.
Her name...
It's Lirin! Wahoo!
[Goku] "The Mightiest Foe."
Hey, Sanzo...
You're hungry!
Wow! How did YOU know?!
That's all you ever do say.
Why don't you try saying
something else for a change, you
predictible little chimp. Eh?
What? Like you don't say the
same things over and over, huh?
[Gojyo] You wanna fight,
stupid monkey?! C'mon!
I double-dog dare ya!
[Goku] I triple-dog dare you!
[Gojyo] I quadruple-dog
dare you!
[Goku] I... whatever the next
dog is without take-backs!
[Sanzo] Don't they know they're
just stuck in another rut?
So what else is new?
[Goku] What the hell is that?
[Gojyo] Don't you know a
boulder when you see one?
I bet it's tasty. Why
don't you try eating it?
[Goku] Shut up!
[Lirin] Hey guys!
No. It can't be...
If it isn't Sanzo's
little... pet.
Lookit, Sanzo has a little pet!
[Sanzo] Peeve. Pet peeve.
I hate her.
HI! I'm back! Ready to
play again you guys?
Whoopee!
[Sanzo] Can't she find
someone else to pester?
I think that one spells
trouble for all of us.
Hey, baldy! I'm gonna
make you cry uncle,
so you better get ready!
Uuuh...
Hey, Sanzo-!
Hey! That's not how
you play the game!
QUIET!
You're so noisey! Stupid dragon.
I should've known better than to
trust that no good Sanzo party.
I swear, no more nice Lirin.
Stupid jerks. They'll be sorry.
Really sorry!
I got it! I know
how to defeat them!
They're coming!
[Hakkai] Holy shit!
What?
It's working! Brilliant Lirin!
I call it Lirin's Project Meat
Buns Master plan! Whoohoo!
Those old farts will be
attracted to buns like bait!
[Goku] Oh, meat
buns! My favorite!
Ha! Perfect!
Where are you going?!
Come back! Baldy!
Monkey! Water Sprite!
Hey! Come back! Are
you listening to me?!
That's so weird! How could they
pass up these tasty meat buns?
What the-?! My meat buns left!
Did you see the way we lifted
these meat buns right out from
under her pointy little nose?
They look so tasty, too!
I can't wait to try them!
Hey, let's hurry up and eat
them before they get cold, okay?
Meat buns are never
half as delicious as
when you eat them warm!
[Trio] Down we go!
On your mark! Get set!
[Trio] Dinner time!
[Lirin] Not so fast!
[Trio] Come again?
Oh oh oh! That really makes me
mad! Give back my meat buns!
Or else I'll-
[Trio] Or else, what?!
[Lirin] You kidding me?
Whacha gonna do to us, huh?
I think you should be a little
more concerned about your own
safety, little girl. See?
We don't cut breaks
for children.
Should I cut breaks for
old fogies like you?
[The three apologize repeatedly]
[Demon 1] We see
how wrong we were!
[Demon 3] We'll do
anything, please forgive
us! We'll do anything!
You'll do anything?
Then you guys can
be my henchmen!
Henchmen?
Sounds good to me, master.
Great! Now what
shall I name you?
But I... already have a-
Porky!
And you're Spot!
Fluffy!
And why should I be Spot?!
And what's with Porky?!
What are we, pets
or something?! Huh?!
[Trio] Perfect!
Let's get this show
on the road, okay?
[Lirin] Wow! You can see the
entire village from up here.
Is this really going
to work, Spot?
[Spot] Yeah...?
Don't worry, you just leave
that to us, little missy!
We might not be as
powerful as you are...
But we rock!
It'll be a cinch to
take care of four bozos!
Consider that jeep stopped!
I see them!
[Goku] Take it back!
You take it back!
[Sanzo] How long can
you guys keep that up?
You take it back!
[Goku] Take it back!
[Hakkai laughs exasperatedly]
Yo, dorks! Let's go!
[Spot] Oh, you're so naughty!
Woo, not bad!
[Trio] India!
[Trio] Give us a ride, will ya?
Yoo-hoo, you alive?
I don't think so.
I'm starving! You got
anything else to eat?
[Owner] Not anymore!
[Fluffy] Yep, that's
them alright.
[Spot] Enjoy your meal
while you can, gentlemen.
We'll hit them before
they suspect anything!
I say we scratch up their jeep!
[Spot] Cut that out!
What on earth is that racket?
[Goku] What are
you doing, Hakkai?
If you don't hurry,
Gojyo's gonna eat it all.
[Gojyo] What'd you say?!
You take that back!
[Goku] No, you take it back!
[Sanzo] For the love of
all that is holy! Shut up!
That sure was close.
Let's mess up their jeep
before they get suspicious.
[Hakuryu whines in distress]
[The Trio repeat "what"
several times in confusion]
Did you just say something?
That wasn't you?
Which means that...
Babies must be sleeping...
in the engine.
That's the stupidest thing...
You've ever said!
[Porky] What was that?
[Spot] I have no idea.
[Fluffy] Sounded kind of
like a baby, didn't it?
Are these the rude,
nasty people who were
picking on you, Hakuryu?
[Hakuryu squeaks in reply]
And you're the one who
ran us over earlier!
No one runs us down and
gets away with it, wise guy!
Prepare to meet our
wrath, one-eyed cyclops!
[Lirin] ♪La la la la la♪
[Trio] Master...
It's no use. Those guys
are much stronger than us.
We can't fight
them head-to-head.
They've gotta have a weakness
of some kind we can exploit.
Weakness?
[Hakkai] Today's been a bit
out of the ordinary, hasn't it?
[Sanzo] Annoying is actually
the term I'd use to describe it.
My stomach's growling.
You're hungry already?!
[Spot] Eek! Demons!
[Spot] Woe is me!
Save us from them!
Get us away from
those awful demons!
Those demons are going
to destory the village!
There must be some big,
strong men around around
to save us, aren't there?
Oh, but where will
we find them?!
[Gojyo] You've gotta be kidding.
[Goku] Those disguises
wouldn't fool anybody!
[Sanzo] You didn't
even shave your legs.
[Hakkai] Poor guys. We
have to punish you again.
But wait! We were told you
guys would never be able to
resist poor, helpless
damsels in distress!
[Gojyo] Come back when
you find some, dumbasses!
Yum! Ooh!
[Trio] Master!
What the hell is going on here?!
Hey, it's you guys!
So hurry up and
tell me how it went!
I'm afraid there's
not much to tell.
Despite my flawless
performance, they simply
didn't buy the others.
No! It was your dumb disguise!
It was because you two bozos
couldn't get into character!
It was because you weren't
in the moment! Don't even
try to lay this all on me!
Oh yeah?! What what was
your movtivation?! I bet
you can't even tell me!
It was all you two's fault!
Why can't you just lure them
outside?! For god's sake.
[Porky] Pardon me, master?
[Lirin] What is it?
Maybe trying to flush them
outside is the problem.
Why don't we just wait and
ambush them instead? Huh?
I already tried that! But they
just run away when they see me!
I think you're forgetting
your new advantage.
This time you have us
to assist you, master.
And you know what that means.
[Trio] We can attack
from all sides!
[Lirin] Attack from all sides?
[Trio] Yes!
[Porky] Attack from all sides!
[Spot] Attack from all sides!
[Fluffy] Attack from all sides!
Attack from all sides!
I can't believe it!
Attack...
From...
All sides!
Spot! Fluffy! Porky!
[Trio] Master!
[Lirin] I'm so happy!
[Tiro] Let's get this
over with and go home.
Why can't we stay
in the village?
Because I've had it up to here
with that little brat, Lirin.
Man. What are the odds?
We'll never be able to get
through driving this way.
I guess we should
just head back.
Okay. Well I'm
fresh out of ideas.
Now this surely can't be good.
Why not?
I think that little girl's
a lot smarter than you, Goku.
[Goku] Don't lump me together
with that little brat!
[The Trio laughs manically]
Not those guys again.
I might actually get tired of
beating them up before they do.
[Spot] How dare you
pulverize us before!
[Fluffy] Yeah! It really hurt!
[Porky] We'll teach
you to do that!
[Trio] ♪Dun dun dun dun!♪
Lirin henchman number one, Spot!
Lirin henchman
number two, Fluffy!
number three, Porky!
[Trio] Now get ready!
It's time to meet your doom!
Check 'em out.
What funny names!
Don't make fun of us!
We're not the ones responsible
for our stupid names!
Yeah, that hurts our feelings!
Yeah, but we can't really expect
them not to laugh at us, can we?
[Spot & Porky] No.
[Lirin laughs]
Looks like I've caught
you, Mr. Baldy! You're
not getting away this time!
What a persistent little...
I envy you, man.
Why don't the chicks persue
me like this, Sanzo?
[Sanzo] I will kill you.
Sanzo! Say your prayers!
Sa...
An...
Zo?
[Spot] Not THE Sanzo who
travels the countryside with his
friends, slaughtering demons?!
[Porky] Oh it can't
be! It just can't be!
This isn't funny, you guys.
A hundred million lives
isn't enough to save us
from the likes of them.
Let's get out of here!
Yeah!
[Lirin] Where do you
think you're going?!
[Trio] Uh-oh...
Don't even think about it!
[Trio] No fair!
STOP CRYING!
Hey fellas, listen to me.
I think I've got an idea.
Here's what we do.
[Fluffy & Porky] I'm listening.
[Spot whispering inaudibly]
[Trio] Yeah!
[Porky] I never thought of that!
I just can't believe we
didn't come up with it sooner.
Well, let's get going!
[Trio] Save us, Sanzo!
[Spot] Nailed it!
We never wanted to do
it, Mr. Sanzo. I swear
on my mother's grave.
The evil witch totured us and
forced us to do what she wanted.
We're one of you guys.
Please! Save us! We're
all at your mercy!
I refuse.
[Gojyo & Goku] Now go away!
[Lirin] Spot, Fluffy, Porky!
How dare you even THINK
about betraying me!
I swear it was a mistake!
It was a mistake!
It was all part of
our grand strategy!
It was?
Oh come on! That was all just
an ingenious part of our clever
ruse to trick them into
putting down their guard.
Right now we have those fools
exactly where we want them.
You know we're telling
the truth. Just look at
these innocent eyes!
[Trio] You see?!
[Trio] Do our eyes lie?
Wow! What a brilliant idea!
Love it!
Stand back while I go
defeat the Sanzo party!
Bye-bye!
[Trio] See ya later!
We make a break for it
the first chance we get.
[Both] Way ahead of ya.
Okay, bald-Sanzo! Here I come!
Goku, you fight her.
Oh, kick ass!
Why'd you choose me?
Makes sense. She's your size.
But Hakkai's the one
who's good with children.
No, no, Gojyo's the one
that's good with women.
Yeah but she's... she's
Sanzo's girlfriend.
You're asking for it.
Now you four jerks
are going to die!
Just like this!
Fine! I'll fight her!
Oh, go cry!
Got ya!
Hey, she kicks ass!
Someone with moves like
that might even be able
to defeat Sanzo party.
If we can help her
do that, we'd be...
[Trio] Be heroes!
Yes! We won't have to
do anything that will
put any of us at risk!
[Both] Right on!
[Trio] After them!
Nailed it again!
Did you see Lirin's moves?
You'll be the ones asking
for mercy now!
We could beat the lot of you
with one of Lirin's little
pinkies! Give up now!
It's futile! Don't
even try to resist!
[Alarm clock rings]
Oh no! Just look at the time!
I better go home before
Yaone gets mad at me!
[Trio] What?!
I have to go now! Bye!
[Lirin] Upsie daisy!
Bye-bye, bald-Sanzo!
I promise we'll play again
real soon, okay guys?
And as you were
saying, guys? Well?
Something about us
asking for mercy.
Oh, no, you got it all wrong!
It was all part of
his grand strategy.
Don't point your
finger at me, dork!
The real brains behind
the grand strategy is
sitting right over there!
That's not true! It's all your
fault for trying to steal those
meat buns in the first place!
It's my fault?!
I've had just about
enough of you.
[Hakkai] This certainly
was no ordinary day.
[Gojyo] So, where are
we staying tonight?
[Goku] I'm hungry. Hey, Sanzo-
[Sanzo] No way.
Hey, calm down! I
just want some food!
We don't want to waste
any more time, Goku.
Man, what the hell?!
You're such a cheapskate!
I know something he
can eat if he wants.
Shut up!
Hey, I wonder how those
three weirdos are holding up?
Who cares?
Tell me again. How did
we get into this mess
in the first place?
All I got out of today
was some bruises.
And I didn't even get
one little meat bun.
[Spot] Hey! I never
got any either!
[Fluffy] I tell you! If I ever
see that little witch again,
I'm going to demand
she treat us to some!
[Porky & Spot] That's right!
She owes us some meat buns!
[Trio] Man, does our life SUCK.
[Goku] Man, what is this,
a tourist group or something?
Nope, it's an armored corps
of demons. Like that's
going to protect them.
Hey, if we beat them
up and strip them,
maybe we could sell their
shields for scrap and
get something to eat!
Any takers? Come on, I'm hungry!
Next time on Saiyuki, we're
"Shielded From our Enemies."