[Zenon] Is the squad
already on the move?
[Shien] Yes. I have sent
two of our best Special
Forces operatives.
[Zenon] Two?
[Shien] Any more would be...
over doing it. Don't you think?
[Zenon] That's true.
Any signs yet of demon activity?
[Shien] I haven't received
any reports as of yet.
Besides...
[Zenon] Besides?
[Shien] I wouldn't think they'd
be anything to worry about.
Do you?
[Zenon] Hmph. Which means
there's nothing for us to
do but just sit here.
[Homura] Not necessarily.
Let's go.
[Zenon] Go? Go where?
To watch them.
[Goku] "The War Prince Returns."
[Gojyo sighs] You know, it feels
like forever since we've had a
chance to relax like this.
[Sanzo] That must mean you have
a really good hand, Gojyo.
[Gojyo] Dagnabit.
You know, come to think of
it, Gojyo's absolutely right.
Seems like any day we
didn't run into a demon,
we ran into a gang of angry,
murderous gods instead.
Ah, excellent!
I'll take that one.
[Goku] Hey, Homura's
a god, isn't he?
What would a god
want with us anyway?
Who knows? He's not nearly as
cute as the babe we ran into
a few months before, huh?
Nor as friendly.
Sanzo, what is your take
on this Homura character?
[Sanzo] Hard to say.
It doesn't change anything.
Whatever their motivations are,
our objective remains the same.
[Gojyo] Keep heading west.
[Sanzo] That's right.
[Goku] West, huh?
[Hakuryu squeaks]
[Goku] I wonder what
Kougaiji's up to?
[Gojyo] Heh. They wouldn't
die if you killed them.
[Goku] Yeah, but...
[Hakkai] There's no use
worrying. What happens happens.
[Sanzo] That pretty
much sums it up.
Anticipating someone else's
move can cost you dearly.
[Sanzo] Kong! I win.
[Sanzo] Damn.
[Goku] Where ya goin', Sanzo?
I wanna go too!
[Sanzo] Do what you want.
I'm not getting food.
[Goku] Aaaaw.
[Hakkai] Where did
those two run off to?
[Gojyo] I think he ran out
to get some cigarettes.
[Hakkai] You think that's wise?
Like Sanzo just said.
None of us know what's waiting
for us just around the corner.
[Gojyo] He can take care
of himself, so let it go.
[Hakkai] I suppose you're right.
How 'bout a game of cards in the
meantime?
[Gojyo] You read my mind.
[Goku] Hey, Sanzo.
[Sanzo] No.
[Goku] Come on, Sanzo!
[Sanzo] Be quiet.
Sanzo!
Shut up.
But Sanzo!
You don't know
what I'll ask you!
Okay then. Just don't ask
something stupid, you got that?
There's a ramen stand over-
See there? That was
a dumb question!
Ow...
[Soldier 1] Genjo
Sanzo, I presume.
Are you all right, Gojyo?
[Gojyo] Yeah, just barely.
Bit excessive, don't you think?
Blowing up an entire
inn like that?
[Gojyo] Sheesh. And I
had a killer hand too.
[Gojyo] Up there!
Is that a demon?
[Hakkai] I believe that's a god.
I'll take care of the sidekicks.
Whoa, shit.
[Sanzo] Damn!
What the-?! Is he taking
the town with us or what?!
[Soldier 1] That's right!
Die!
Hey, Hakkai, what are
we running for anyway?
We've got to try to draw his
fire away from the village.
Besides...
Damn, they mean business too.
Besides, what?
[Hakkai] I'm worried
about Sanzo and Goku.
[Gojyo] What for?
Well, I'm afraid those two
just might destroy the
entire village.
I didn't get supplies yet.
Uh oh.
Buckle your seatbelt.
I'm gonna have to start
hauling serious ass.
[Soldier 1] This is it?
Is what it?!
I expected so much more from
you four so-called heroes.
It appears that we have
gravely overestimated the
legendary Sanzo party.
[Sanzo] Oh, you did, did you?
Estimate this!
Good job!
[Sanzo] You're one of
Homura's thugs, aren't you?
Talk! What are they after?
[Goku & Sanzo] What?!
[Goku] What'd you do that for?!
Isn't he one of your comrades?!
Any one of us would gladly give
up our lives for Lord Homura.
One life is meaningless
when compared to Homura's
greater cause.
[Soldier 2 yells in pain]
Moron. That's what you get for
pausing in the middle of battle
to make pretty speeches.
I hope you two weren't hurt.
[Goku] Yeah, we're okay.
[Hakkai chuckles]
[Hakkai] You know,
come to think of it,
it had been too
quiet lately.
[Gojyo] People just don't tire
of trying to kill us, do they?
[Gojyo sighs deeply]
[Hakkai] It's not easy
being a celebrity.
[Sanzo] And the real stalkers
have yet to make an appearance.
[Gojyo & Hakkai] Huh?
[Goku] Homura!
[Jiroushin] You're not observing
the Lower World again, are you?
[Goddess] Of course.
Can you think of a better
way to pass the time?
Sure beats the
drudgery that passes
for entertainment up here.
Be more careful. It's extremely
dangerous to say such things.
[Goddess] It's starting.
[Jiroushin] Lady?
The sequel to the battle between
outlaws and misfits has begun.
Wouldn't you like
a ringside seat?
[Jiroushin] My Lady...
To say such things.
[Goddess] I can't wait
to see what happens next.
Long time no see.
Not long enough.
I'm just watching. I wanted
to see you guys fight.
Looks like you got what you
came for. You can go now.
Phenomenal...
is what'd I'd like
to say, but...
I'm afraid you're not
quite there yet.
Son Goku, the same goes for you.
Only a god... would
be so melodramatic.
Come on, what do you want?
Don't you worry. We're
just here to watch today.
Does that mean you're
just going to take off?
Why don't you stay and
play a little while?
I really don't think you and
your friends are prepared for
this level of fighting yet.
Oh please. That little skirmish
wasn't even an appetizer.
[Zenon] I'm glad to hear it.
I'd hate to have come all
the way out here for nothing.
[Goku] Okay then!
Stop talking and
let's get it on!
What?!
Hold it. Looks like you boys
will be fighting us today.
It is Homura's wish that none of
you interfere with this process.
[Hakkai] You're awfully
confident in your abilities.
[Gojyo] It's three against two,
guys. Don't think about begging
for forgiveness later,
'cause I won't be in the mood.
Heh.
I'm not the begging type.
[Sanzo] Keep your guard up.
They're losers, but
they're still gods.
[Gojyo] You don't have to
tell me, man. I've got eyes.
[Hakkai] All you have to do is
look at them to see we've got
a real fight on our hands.
[Sanzo] I'm just saying.
[Gojyo] Stop stalling.
[Hakkai] Shall we go then?
[Goku] There!
Take that!
What's the matter, Goku?
Surely, you ought to be
able to at least touch me.
Come now!
Show me some of
your true mettle.
Don't get too cocky!
[Homura] Be strong, Son Goku!
[Hakkai groans in strain]
[Hakkai] He's not giving
me a chance to lower my
defensive barrier!
I've got to find a way
to go on the offensive.
[Shien] How long do you
intend to hide behind
this protective shield?
Maintaining your chi
cannot be easy.
Lay off him!
Try that on for size!
Hakkai?
[Zenon chuckles]
Well, I guess you won't
be drinking for a while.
Kenren...
[Single gunshot]
You're not so high and
mighty after all...
are you?
[Homura] Don't hold back.
It's the only way
you'll grow stronger.
[Goku] It's just too much.
None of the guys I've
fought before even come
close to this guy.
He's not even trying!
Is that all you've got?
You kidding? Hell no!
That wasn't bad.
But you're too obvious.
Don't let me anticipate.
Well, smartass. Let's see if
you can anticipate this move-!
You should be aware...
you're facing a rather
critical decision here.
Why... why you...
This guy won't give
us a break, Sanzo.
How much ammo does that
thing have anyway?
Whining, are we?
Yeah, right. I just don't like
being toyed with, that's all.
Me either. I won't be
happy until the gods
have been dethroned.
And I don't like leaving
Goku with that guy.
Well that certainly is a first.
We're all in agreement for once.
Right, let's go!
[Goku] They're... beating
the crap out of us.
Oh no...
What should I do?
[Homura] Aren't you
going to take it off?
Take it off. Why not fight
me at your full potential?
[Goku] I won't do it.
I'd rather die than take
it off for the likes of you!
So be it, Son Goku.
I'm gonna do it this time!
I've only got one more chance!
HALT!
No...
Grow stronger.
You must grow stronger,
Son Goku.
Goku!
Zenon, Shien. Let's go.
No way!
Man, if you say so.
[Shien] Is this really
what you want, Homura?
[Sanzo] Hold it! You're not
planning on leaving unfinished
business again, are you?
Quit toying with us and
let's get this over with!
[Homura] I've done
everything I've come to do.
[Gojyo] I thought you
wanted our Scripture?
Well come and get it, big guy.
[Homura] If I took
the Scripture now,
what excuse would I have
to come see you again?
Isn't that right, Konzen?
[Shien] Homura, you realize,
to leave now would only
constrain their progress.
As of a chain, as those
shackles on your wrists.
[Zenon] Jeez, it's not easy
keeping up with his whims.
[Homura] So long.
[Hakkai] Goku! Are
you all right?!
[Gojyo] Goku!
Huh?
[Hakkai] Goku... Goku!
[Goku whines softly in pain]
[Hakkai] Better take it easy.
You took a hell of
a beating last night.
Oh, right.
I lost... I remember.
Yeah. He really
whipped your ass.
What a loser.
[Goku] Hey, screw
you! I'm no loser.
[Gojyo] No, you're a
weak-ass beat-up monkey.
[Goku] Like you
could do any better!
[Gojyo] What did you say?!
[Sanzo] He's right, you know.
We're in no position
to talk, no.
We're all completely
at their mercy.
[Goku] I've made up my mind.
I know he's stronger than I
am, but next time I see him...
I promise, I won't lose again.
[Gojyo] In that case,
you better concentrate on
getting your strength back.
[Hakkai] Come to think of it,
I did see a nice Chinese
restaurant nearby.
[Goku] Now that you mention
it, I am kind of hungry!
[Sanzo] Thanks a lot, Hakkai!
Now we'll never
hear the end of it!
[Goku] Come on, guys!
Just an order of eggrolls!