[Hakkai] It's been three
months since we left Chang'an,
yet we still have
a long way to go.
And you're forgetting we still
know very little about the
experiments to revive Gyumaoh.
We have no time to
waste on fool's errands.
And yet I don't feel any part
of this journey has been
wasted, you know what I mean?
I guess...
[Gojyo] Hey, guys.
Check this out.
Isn't it somethin'?
[Goku] It's more
beautiful than a meat bun!
[Gojyo] That's quite
an endorsement.
[Hakkai] Come to think of it,
we're always heading towards
the setting sun, aren't we?
Ah, sweet youth!
[Gojyo begins laughing
hysterically]
[Gojyo] Ah, sweet youth!
It wasn't that bad, now was it?
[Sanz] No time has
been wasted, huh?
[Sanzo] Everyone, let's go!
[Hakkai] Yes, let's.
[Gojyo] In we go!
[Goku] Yippee!
We can see sunsets everyday.
[Goddess] For as
long as you live.
But I wonder, are
you still alive?
Your blood flows, you breathe,
but without emotion, you are
nothing but an empty shell.
As soulless as a
cold, dead corpse.
How long can you live
like this, Nataku?
The memories of that brat's
crimes were sealed away
in the vaults of Heavens
more than 500 years ago.
He can't remember
Tenpou or Kenren.
Or Konzen. Nor even you or me.
Well, you asked for this
cruel fate, but I wonder
just how long you can wait.
Now that you have turned
into this blank slate.
Your soul lives alone.
All alone and condemned to
live enternally in the past.
[Goku] "Silent Cry".
I'm so bored!
Come to think of it,
we haven't run into a
demon for some time now.
Yeah, and I'm totally
out of shape!
How about I give
you a refresher course,
[Gojyo] how's that, huh?!
[Goku] Shut up!
How inane can an
argument possibly get?
Lighten up. They're just
keeping themselves occupied.
What the-?!
Aw man, did we
run over somebody?
You said you were
looking for some action,
I think we found it.
The notorious Sanzo
company, I presume?
So what if we are?
Then standing before you
is the Armored Demon Corps,
under the Kougaiji's command.
Why should I care?
Because my Lord has ordered
me to let you state my steel!
Ready men?!
Attack!
[Goku] Bring it on!
[Kougaiji] What's
the meaning of this?!
How dare you send an
Armored Demon Corps
after the Sanzo party
without even consulting me?!
[Koshu] I didn't expect to
see you after that pathetic
performance in your
last encounter.
I'm surprised you can
even show your face.
I do hope your wounds
are healing nicely.
[Kougaiji] But they'll be
slaughtered, and for what?
[Koshu] Why not? What did those
fools have to live for anyway?
I did them a favor,
if you ask me.
And besides, take a look.
Our efforts to revive Gyumaoh
have entered a new phase.
[Kougaiji] Come to think
of it, this equipment
wasn't here than before.
Amazing...
How I never get use
to the sight of him.
[Koshu] I think your talents
might be put to better use if
you focused your energies
on searching for the
scriptures, don't you?
So, in other words, I don't want
you wasting any more time on
the Sanzo party. Are we clear?
[Kougaiji] That's absurd!
[Koshu] Don't make me remind
you that Gyumaoh can only be
awakened if we obtain the five
Scriptures of Heaven and Earth
the gods used for the
creation of the world.
I want you to find
them, Kougaiji.
The Seiten Scripture of Koumyou
Sanzo that governs evolution.
The Maten Scripture of
Genjo Sanzo that consigns
all power to oblivion.
And the other three
scattered about the globe.
Find them all, and
bring them to me.
Oh? What's wrong? I thought
you would be pleased.
[Kougaiji] Pleased?!
[Koshu] Yes.
[Koshu] It means you'll
be able to free your
mother that much sooner.
Depending, of course, on how
quickly you complete your task.
That had better be the truth.
Who knows? You can register
any complaints you might
have when the mission's
finally completed.
Hurry on now. And by the way.
Do keep Lirin from venturing
outside the castle too much.
She is our one and
only daughter after
all, isn't that right?
I mean, we can't be too
careful. That makes her
very precious indeed.
We're no longer allowed
to pursue Sanzo?
This can't be for real.
She has ordered us to locate
the other Sanzos and get hold
of their scriptures first.
From now on, all our efforts are
supposed to be focused there.
If this turns out to be
the quickest way to end
this idiotic experiment,
then so be it.
[Dokugakuji] And what? Are
we going to just jump and do
exactly what the she-fox says?
Don't get me wrong. I'm not so
keen on following orders either.
But if we don't do this,
even more people will die.
You're right.
[Kougaiji] Yaone.
I want you to stay
here with Lirin.
What for?
[Kougaiji] I've got
a bad feeling.
I don't want you to leave
her side, understand?
[Yaone] Yes, My Lord.
[Dokugakuji] Wait, are you...
Are we really giving up
on going after Sanzo?
[Kougaiji] Only in appearance.
Don't worry. They won't
be so easy to kill.
I will not allow anyone else
to have my revenge for me.
I still have a lot of payback.
And I want to be the
one to give it to them.
It's not over.
This one's mine!
Aw man, this is too easy!
Don't be so selfish, Goku!
Be sure to save some
for me now, will ya?
My turn!
You better watch
your ass, Goku.
A few more moves like that and
I just might catch up with you.
I sure like your style, Hakkai.
[Gojyo] Hm. Sanzo's gun seems
to disintegrate their armor.
Got 'em all!
[Rashu] They're even more
powerful than the legends say!
[Hakkai] Hey big guy!
So what's it going to be?
I think you ought to call
it a day, don't you?
I've no need...
...of mercy!
Sanzo!
You okay, Sanzo?!
Well, that was overkill.
Boy, we sure did leave a mess.
[Gojyo] And trash pickup
isn't until Thursday.
[Sanzo] Leave it.
I'm sure some idiot
will pick it up.
Awesome! What a cool helmet!
I bet we could trade
it for some meat buns.
[Sanzo] Put that down!
Okay, so how do I look?
Loser.
[Rashu begins
laughing maniacally]
Get it off me!
What did he do now?!
Oh no!
That little idiot!
Help Sanzo!
Goku!
[Rashu] I have you now, Sanzo!
What the-?!
What-what's happening?!
[Gojyo] Holy shit!
Where the hell am I?
[Rashu] I see you
are finally awake.
[Sanzo] So you didn't die?
[Rashu] My physical
body was destroyed, yes.
What you see before you is the
entrance to the world beyond.
Please don't continue on
your way on my account.
My orders are to take the Maten
Scripture you carry and deliver
it immdediately to Houtou
Castle, and I intend to.
But unfortunately, it has taken
all the energy I have to
lock you away in this place,
so that will have to wait.
My, that is a real bummer.
Excuse me if I'm not impressed
by your loyal service.
I'm not finished with you yet.
My soul still lives.
I could easily take
control of your body,
and there's nothing you
could do to prevent me from
carrying the scriptures back
to Houtou Castle on
your own two feet.
Ha! How absurd!
I'd like to see you try.
[Rashu laughs]
[Goku] Sanzo!
Damn it! Why can't he hear me?!
Hey Sanzo!
[Gojyo] It looks
like a giant turd.
You are so grossing
me out, you know that?
[Goku] Sanzo!
[Gojyo] Did you...?
[Hakkai] I heard it too!
Goku's definitely
inside that thing.
How the hell do we get in there?
Do you think we should
try to destroy it?
We might hurt whoever's inside.
[Gojyo] What choice do we have?
[Rashu] Very good, Sanzo.
You have a strong mind.
But in the end, you
can not stop it.
Finding your weakness will
simply be a matter of time.
Sorry, but I don't recall
having any weakness.
Perhaps not now, but
what of your past?
What do you think I'd find if I
probed deep into your memories?
I do wonder.
I'll bet that's where
I'll find your weakness.
Don't... be...
[Sanzo] Koumyouo...
[Kouryou] Excuse me, master.
[Koumyoou] What is it?
I don't understand. Why are
you smoking out here in the open
where someone's sure to see you?
I guess, it's just such
a lovely autumn day.
Yes it is, but what does that
have to do with anything?
There's really no harm done,
as long as nothing burns.
Yeah, I guess. But if you
burn all these leaves for me,
I won't have to rake them.
Kouryuu, the river rat. That's
what they call you, isn't it?
It's not a very nice name.
Anyone who calls you that
is a monk in name only.
He is not your friend.
[Kouryou] It's alright.
It doesn't bother me.
I'm used to being called
things like that.
And besides, to be honest, I
actually kind of like my name.
[Sanzo] Kouryuu,
a name referring to
the Changjiang river.
How could I take offense to
being compared to something
so grand and majestic.
I don't understand you
at all, not in the least.
I know that the Buddha
extols the Heavenly virtues
of preserving all life,
but you not only risked
your own life to save me
from that raging river,
but you took me in,
and kept me at your side.
It was because of the
sound of your voice.
[Kouryou] Huh?
[Koumyou] You called out
to me, repeatedly.
You called out so many
times. I had never seen
such will in a child before.
[Sanzo] I cried out to
him, and he heard me.
You were so noisy, I
had to take you with me.
You were driving me crazy.
I'm sorry, I don't
quite understand.
One day, Kouryou, you will
hear a voice all out to you.
Then you will understand.
[Kouryou] If I ever
did hear that voice,
I would take him in, too.
I would teach him discipline
and obedience with my fan.
I could save him.
Man, this giant shit pile ain't
easy to break into. It's tough.
Those soldiers might have
been easy to defeat.
Their armor on the
other hand seems to
be a whole nother story.
[Gojyo] Actually, there was one
of us who was able to do it.
If that's the case, then...
[Gojyo] The only person
who can save Sanzo is Sanzo.
Then I'll guess we
just have to wait.
[Abbott] You say burglars
broke into Master Sanzo's
room last night,
murdered him, and took
the Seiten Scripture?
Is this what you're saying?
Speak. Speak up child.
[Kouryou] Yes, that's
how it happened.
Abbott, please allow me to
make up for my negligence by
granting me leave so that
I may avenge my master and
reclaim the Seiten Scripture.
Last night, my master bestowed
the holy name right before
he passed away.
Genjo Sanzo, that is my
name from this day forth.
Then this must be Buddha's will.
With Koumyou Sanzo's gold
crown, I hereby recognize you
as Priest Toua Genjo
Sanzo the thirty first,
formal heir to the Seiten
and Maten Scriptures,
two of the five founding
parchments of heaven and earth.
All kinds of monsters and evil
spirits inhabit these mountains.
It's too dangerous for you
to travel unarmed. But that,
at least, can
easily be rectified.
[Kouryou] What is this is?
[Abbott] It is the
temple armory. You may
take whatever you like.
Choose well, and remember,
the most terrify beings
often walk the earth as men.
This is all I need.
[Abbott] As you wish.
[Sanzo] A weapon small
enough to aim at my own
temple. If it came to that.
I found it!
The losing the master you
loved and revered, you
fled down the mountain.
Frightened, uncertain,
and alone! You murdered
countless others,
until you eventually found
yourself unable to see the value
in any life, including yours!
[Goku] Sanzo!
No! I-I can't reach him!
Sanzo...
Not again!
I'm trapped and
I can't reach him!
[Rashu] A monk of the order,
with his hands stained in blood.
Hypocrite. How many of Buddha's
teachings have you perverted?
What sacred writing have you
twisted to justify your sins?
How do you keep living?!
I can hear a voice.
What?!
[Sanzo] Do you have
anything more to say?
No matter how red my
hands become, blood
can be washed away.
That is how we continue living.
[Hakkai] Sanzo?!
[Gojyo] Goku?
You found a way out!
After some silly psychoanalysis.
What were you guys
doing in there?
Listening.
Listening for a voice.
[Koumyou] One day,
Kouryou, you will hear
a voice call out to you.
Then you will understand.
What are you looking at?
[Sanzo] How could I possibly
ignore someone so noisey?
[Goddess] If people must
kill in order to live, the
blood can be washed away.
How, Merciful Goddess, do
they survive with such a
warped sense of morality?
Jiroushin, do you know why we,
the gods, exist here in Heaven?
It's not to look down on them,
but to watch over them.
To watch over those
who were born to live!
[Jiroushin] So do you approve
of how things are going?
I just told you that
I'm not here to sit
in judgment, Jiroushin.
I could never change who
they are in a million years.
Isn't that right, Nataku?
They have no shortage of
challenges ahead of them.
So ride west, Sanzo.
No matter what you may
run into along the way.
Head west, even if you
leave behind a trail corpses.
[Sanzo] To live in the moment.
To protect the ones we love.
To change the future.
Those are the reason these
men fought through eternity.
And now the curtain
rises on a new battle.
"Descends, the Prince of War",
in the next episode of Saiyuki.