NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and lead the night grave of 100
demons, was known as the
Supreme Commander of the yokai.
They had another name for him.
The Lord of
Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
-Why the long face?
-I-- I couldn't protect her.
-So, you want to become strong?
-Yeah, I guess so.
-You don't even know
what being strong means,
yet you wanna be strong, huh?
-Huh?
-Those things are
a damn nuisance.
-Lord Zen, here you are.
I've been looking for you.
You mustn't overexert yourself.
-I know.
NARRATOR: An eerie shadow
lurks through the morning mist.
The footsteps of beings
not of this world
suddenly approach
the Nura mansion.
-Supreme commander,
Lord Zen is here!
[panting]
-Oh, Lord Zen!
What a pleasant surprise!
-Oh, hey Yuki-Onna
-I'm glad you've come.
-Thank you, it's been quite
a while, Supreme Commander.
-Rikuo should be returning
home shortly, too.
ZEN: Excellent, I'm
greatly looking forward
to seeing the third.
-Mm-hmm.
-I'm afraid he hasn't been
formally installed yet.
It's a little premature
to call him that.
-I see nothing wrong with
addressing him respectfully
by his future honorific.
He'll bear the responsibilities
of Nura Clans third air
soon enough.
-That Rikuo is giving
me such a hard time.
I've told him time
and time again
it is his duty to succeed
me and become a yokai.
One completely devoted to evil.
-I'm home.
-Wait a minute, where'd you
get those expensive sweets?
-Oh, Rikuo, don't tell me you
went to school again, huh?
-Don't tell me you
went out and stole them
from somewhere again.
I told you I wanted you to
go easy on the evil deeds!
And I don't care that
your signature move
is to take things
without being noticed.
-Master, you've
got it all wrong.
These sweets are a generous
gift from Lord Zen.
-Huh?
Lord Zen is here right now?
-Mm-hmm.
-He's in the parlor?
-You guys ate my share of mangu.
-I wonder why he's here.
-Master?
-Uh, yes?
-It's been such a long time.
Master, it is I, Zen.
-Greetings, Lord Zen.
It's good to see you.
[laughs]
-No need to be so formal.
Call me Zen.
-So who is that yokai anyway?
-Yes, and how does
he know our master?
-He's the head of the Zen Group.
He used to come and
play with Master Rikuo
when he was little.
He was like a big
brother to the Master.
-Excuse me?
I have brought some tea for you.
[boing]
[crash]
-Oh no, master, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
[wind]
-Yukeona!
What are you doing?
How dare you treat
Master Rikuo my sworn
brother with disrespect!
There will be no mercy for you!
-Please forgive me!
-Well, now that we've
got that out of the way,
what pranks have you
pulled today, Master?
-Uh, none.
-By the way, I'm
very sorry I haven't
been able to attend the
clan's general assembly.
-Huh?
Oh, don't worry about that.
All they do there is brag
about their latest evil deeds.
-Now, now, Master,
you know you really
mustn't be saying
things like that.
After all, we both know
that you will one day
become the leader of all yokai.
-Uh--
-Personally, I can't
wait for the glorious day
when you finally take over
as the rightful third era
of the Nura Clan.
-Stop it, Zen.
I'm not the successor, OK?
Besides, I'm human.
-Don't you lie to me!
I've heard every one
of the rumors, Rikuo!
[gasp]
-Many in the clan believe that
you're some kind of a coward,
and that none of the top brass
supports you as the heir.
-Oh, you knew all that?
-Of course I knew.
So why don't you tell me
what's going on with you.
-Well, wouldn't it be weird
if the leader of all yokai
was human?
That's why I can't
be the successor.
It's impossible.
-Impossible?
I will kill you,
you cowardly fool!
When did you turn
into such a weakling!
-Stop him, someone!
[yelling]
-Lord Zen's wings are
poisonous, don't touch them!
-I didn't pledge my life
to serve a loser like you!
[coughs]
-Lord Zen!
-Get away!
-Um, excuse me?
Is Rikuo at home right now?
Oh?
[wind howling]
-Oh, wow!
What was that?
-The Ayakashi known as
Zen is a bird yokai,
leader of the Zen Group, and a
master of potions and poisons.
When its wings are
soaked in sake,
they turn into a
deadly poison that
causes the internal
organs to fester.
Any medicine can
turn toxic over time.
Similarly, members
of the Zen group
are said to be
beautiful at birth.
But as they reach manhood,
their wings and feathers
change into that of poison.
However, perhaps due
to this special treat,
this Yokai group
is physically weak,
and at any time could fade away.
They are ephemeral,
fragile yokai.
-Are you feeling
all right, Lord Zen?
The third heir to the
Nura Clan is nothing more
than a spineless
and immature fool.
After you went through
such pains to see him.
-Let us succeed and break
away from the Nura Clan.
You do not need the
influence of the Nura
to make it on your own.
-You asked him to
come, didn't you?
-Huh?
-Well, I suppose
you figured it out.
-What the heck
were you thinking?
Lord Zen should not be
traveling in his condition.
You're terrible!
-Terrible, huh?
If that is what you think of
me, what you believe I am,
you won't inherit my Nura Clan.
-Good, because that's exactly
what I've been begging you for.
And by the way, it's
not your Nura Clan.
It's just a bunch of
trouble making yokai.
-Master Rikuo, you
are sadly mistaken.
ZEN: Thank you, Hebidayu.
We the Zen group, are greatly
indebted to the Nura Clan.
My father, my
grandfather, and myself
were all physically weak.
It was none other than Master
Nurarihyon and his clan
who went out of their
way to protect us.
And they treated us
equally as fellow yokai
-This is a map of
the Nura Clan's night
parade of 100 demons.
Here is the Nura Clan.
There are many
other yokai groups
which are affiliated
with our clans.
Lord Mokugyo Daruma's Daruma
Group, and Lord Zen's Zen
Group, for example.
From ancient times, Japan
has been home to many yokai.
Yokai of the sea, the mountains,
and inanimate objects.
Nearly every one of
them are weak creatures
who dwell within the darkness,
protecting all those yokai who
are weak has been one of the
duties of Master Nurari's
Jones' Nura Clan.
-I have no more desire
to uphold that honor.
Not to that boy.
And the supreme commander
is getting older.
Perhaps the end of
the Nura Clan is near.
-As is yours.
-Huh?
-Karasu Tengu, do
you really think
we can catch up
to the Gloom Cart?
-Yes, just leave
everything to me.
Master, come this way.
It's the shortcut.
-I should have been
more honest with them
and told them how I really felt.
-Hebidayu.
I suppose the anti-Rikuo
faction put you up to this.
-No doubt Zen will ally
himself with Rikuo.
-Yes.
-If you cannot handle him,
I will send reinforcements.
-I assure you
won't be necessary.
I can handle that pathetic
weakling all by myself.
Besides, I get the
pleasure of finishing off
someone who was once my boss.
-Master Rikuo.
I see them.
-So there they are.
-Please wait.
Something is amiss.
-What happened to
that pledge you
made when we exchanged
cuts of loyalty.
-Loyalty?
What are you talking about?
-You are a pitiful,
cowardly traitor.
-The way I see it,
you betrayed me first.
-How's that?
-I would have enjoyed
my current position
if you had bothered to become
more powerful and influential.
But no, you always put
the Nura Clan first,
it was always for their sake.
You don't have a shred of
ambition in your weak body.
I'm sick of you.
-Guess what, They'll have no
use for you once I'm dead.
-That may be true.
When that happens, so be it.
But now, this is
what I have to do.
-I see.
But I still have unfinished
business to take care of.
[coughs]
-You're talking about that
idiot son of the Nura Clan.
You're still harping
on about him.
-I can't-- I can't let you
kill me here in the middle
of nowhere, I refuse
to let it happen.
-Flap your little wings and
fight as much as you like,
but right now your going to die!
-Karasu Tengu.
-Lord Zen, are you all right?
-What are you doing out here?
-I had to apologize to you.
I wanted to make you
understand, so I came after you.
-Where are your bodyguards?
You know that I'm not
capable of protecting you.
-Karasu Tengu, who is that?
-An officer of the
Zen Group, Hebidayu.
-What a perfect opportunity.
I'll kill Nurarihyon's
grandson and win ultimate glory
for myself as the head of
the new Hebidayu group.
-Hebidayu, you're unforgivable.
Rikuo, get away.
You can't win against him.
-Die!
-Rikuo!
-You just stay still.
-What the?
You're--
-If you had within even
an ounce of Zen's honor,
I might have at least spared
your miserable little life.
-Just who are you?
-It's Master Rikuo.
-That's Rikuo?
-Zen, what's up?
ZEN: I see.
So the stories of you being
one-fourth yokai are true.
And yet here I am,
full-fledged, full-blooded yokai
and yet I was totally helpless.
Hey Rikuo, the way
you are right now,
you could become
the third, you know?
It would be great to
see you lead the clan.
While I'm still alive.
-You wanna drink?
-Yes, I'd like that.
Would you pour one for me?
-I feel bad about
Hebidayu, and it's all
because I'm such a weak leader.
It must've been
unbearably hard on him.
Exchange sake cups
with me, Rikuo.
I want to officially
become your sworn brother.
If i'm going to die anyway
I want to die serving you,
and no one else.
-You sure about that?
-I am.
And I'll stake whatever
life I have left on you.
As you are now.
-All right, you're a weak
yokai, so I'll protect you.
And you will support me.
Besides, there's a good reason
why you can't die, isn't there?
-So, you were eavesdropping?
-Heh.
-How mischievous of you.
-Ah--
-Karasu.
-Yes, Master?
-With how many yokai must
I exchange cups of loyalty
before they acknowledge me?
-Huh?
I am going to become
the third heir.
-Yes sir!
What a pity, when dawn
breaks, he'll become human.
[sobs]
-Such a pity indeed!
-I'm off to school!
-Hurry up!
-Right!
-Can you do me a favor?
Rikuo forgot to take
his lunch again.
-Oh sure, of course I will.
Huh?
-The other two lunches
are for you and Aotabo.
I'm sorry, I mean they are
for Kurata and you, Tsurara.
-Thank you.
We're off!
-Ah, man.
My head feels all fuzzy.
What exactly
happened last night?
Ah, good morning Kana.
-Ah, good morning.
Guess we both got
here early today.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): It's nice
whenever I get to see Kana,
it makes me feel
like a normal human.
-Ah, hi guys.
I haven't seen you
since that night.
-Hey, Kiyotsugu.
-Both of you saw those
things there, didn't you?
-Huh?
-Uh, saw what?
They were supposed
to have been there,
inside the old school building.
I mean yokai!
Right?
You saw the yokai, right Rikuo?
-(GASPING) I can't breathe!
-So then are you
saying that you didn't
see these yokai yourself?
-Huh?
Who are you?
-My name's Tsurara Oikawa.
The two of you are Kiyotsugu
and Shima from the next class,
aren't you?
-So, Tsurara Oikawa, huh?
-Maybe you panicked and ran
away and didn't see them?
-No, not at all.
I stayed until the very
end, but regretfully I
didn't see anything.
So I guess there
weren't any yokai there.
No yokai in the old
school building.
[laughs]
-Yuki-Onna.
-Oh, Master!
From now on, please
don't leave for school
without the two of us with you.
Oh, and take this.
It's your lunch box.
Your mother asked us to make
sure that you've got it.
-What are you doing?
-I don't want you hanging
around me like that.
-I will always be by your side.
-I just want to spend my
days at school in peace.
-Yes, I promise no
one in school will
learn the secret of your body.
-The-- the secret of my body?
What does that mean?
-Hmm.
-Uh-- All right, fine.
But just don't call me Master
here or outside of the house,
OK?
-OK, I won't.
And you can go ahead
and call me Tsurara.
-Tsu-- Tsurara?
-Yes.
-I've seen them in somewhere.
Why is she bringing
him his lunch?
I guess there's a lot of things
I don't know about Rikuo.
-I'm from Kyoto.
My name is Yura Keikain.
It's nice to meet all of you.
-She's so pretty.
[sigh]
-Rikuo had no recollection
of having transformed.
And what is the true
identity of this strange girl
who suddenly appeared?
[theme music]
-Do you know why Master's
hair stands sideways
in its night form?
-Huh?
Why, why?
-I hear it's simply because
his head is long to the side.
-That's just terrible.
-Next time, Yura Keikain and
the Kiyojuji Paranormal Patrol.