-In days of old,
people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
demons was known as the
Supreme Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for him.
The Lord of Pandemonium.
Norarihyon.
[theme music - in japanese]
-I, too, was once human.
One who fought because
he wanted to live.
However, humans do not have the
power to stand up to demons!
[grunt]
-Tell me, Rikuo.
Will you continue to
reject the way of a Yokai
and live your life
completely as a human?
If so, I will risk
my very existence
and kill you right now!
But if you intend to become
the third heir, the Supreme
Commander of the Nura
Clan, and live as a Yokai,
then show that
resolve and defeat me.
Give yourself over
to evil, Rikuo.
Abandon your humanity.
As I did!
[grunting]
-Hear me.
I am going to become
the third heir, Gyuki!
Ya!
-Oh!
Oh.
[gasping]
-Well done.
Master Rikuo.
[rain falling]
[grunting]
-Rikuo.
-I'm here.
-Listen carefully.
Mount Nejireme is the western
border of the Nura clan.
The clan has no influence with
other Yokai beyond that point.
From here, I can
see it all clearly.
Unless we act now, our
clan will fall apart
from within and without.
That is the reason
for all my actions.
I won't tolerate anyone who
dares to try and destroy
my beloved Nura clan.
Even if that person is you.
-Master Rikuo!
What is the meaning of all this?
-Master Rikuo.
What happened in here?
-Gyuki.
Have you gone insane?
-You filthy traitor!
-Wait.
-Please do not stop us, master.
-Master.
He dared turn his sword on you.
-Yes.
And I do not regret my actions.
[gasp]
-Can you really blame me?
The future of the Nura
clan was about to be
entrusted to a fool.
A fool who refuses to
accept that he is a Yokai.
But I was wrong.
You were able to defeat me.
You have proven to have
the skills and the will.
-Master Rikuo.
Please step back from him.
-He's still dangerous.
-It seems there's no need
for further consideration.
-Master!
-And now this is
my final decision.
[gasps]
-Why did you stop me, Rikuo?
Why?
I must take
responsibility for this
as the one who plotted treason.
Why didn't you just let me die?
Now I'll never be able
to face Gozu and Mezu.
-Gyuki.
You've made your reasons
quite painfully clear.
Once you confirmed
I was weak, you
would kill me and then yourself.
But I turned out
to be legitimate,
and yet you still chose death.
That is very much like you.
But you know what?
There's no need to die.
This is nothing.
-What is Master thinking?
-This is a very
serious incident.
-Gyuki.
Live.
You hear me?
I won't allow a
member of my clan
to die over a small
matter like this one.
[gasp]
-You can get more answers
from my human form.
If you're not satisfied, then
do whatever you feel is right.
You can kill me for all I care.
GYUKI (VOICEOVER):
I lost my father
when I was five years old.
And I was separated from
my mother was I was seven.
I barely remember them.
That's all the more reason
why Lord Norarihyon's words
from that day still remain
deep within my heart.
-All right.
Let me be your
father from now on.
Umewakamaru.
GYUKI (VOICEOVER):
At that moment,
the Nura clan became my family.
[grunting]
-Oh!
You're up.
Well, now.
You're looking much better.
-You really do change
back to your other form
when morning comes.
-That's right.
I'm human now.
-Do you remember what happens
to you during the night?
-Yes, I remember.
All about Hebidayu and
about the Kyuso clan.
And Mount Nejireme I know
about all the things I did.
When I'm my Yokai form,
my blood seems to boil.
And I lose control of myself.
-Rikuo.
You know you're a--
-I know.
I really am a Yokai.
Maybe it's time I
made up my mind.
Honestly, I want
to live in peace.
But there are people
I need to protect.
And I know I'm going to have to
rely on this blood to do that.
So you see, if there's
someone like you around who I
can trust, someone who
loves this clan so much--
I want them to stay and
be a part of the family.
-Family.
-Yeah.
Anyway, you just get some rest.
NORARIHYON (VOICEOVER): Let
me be your father from now on.
Omewakamaru.
-Hmm.
-Master.
How is Lord Gyuki's
condition this morning?
-Well, he seems to be
doing a lot better today.
I think that he's
going to be just fine.
-Are you sure
about this, Master?
Allowing somebody who rebelled
and turned his sword on you
to stay in the clan?
-But isn't Gyuki a
member of our family?
-Mmm.
-Oh, by the way.
Kana and the others.
Are they OK?
-Yes.
You don't have to
worry about them.
They're fine.
-We got all of them back
home, safe and sound.
-Grr!
Why did you take us to
such an awful place?
-Yeah.
When the Yokai
came to attack us,
I thought we were all done for.
[laughter]
-Now, now.
Honestly, I'm quite
jealous of you all.
I really wish I could have
seen it with my own eyes.
-So what were they like?
-I don't know, and I don't
want to remember, either.
-Yeah, no kidding.
I never want to go through
anything that scary again
as long as I live.
I wonder why Nura didn't
show up for school today.
Maybe he's hiding something.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
-I think this is going to
warrant further investigation.
-It's strange.
He wasn't at all scary.
Like that rat Yokai was.
-Is something wrong, Ienaga?
-Oh.
Um, no.
Nothing at all.
-All right, everyone.
It's time for all of us to go
out again and search for Yokai!
-Yes, sir!
-Oh, come on.
You've got to be joking.
-Really?
-I'd be happy to go out
and look for more Yokai.
-Huh?
-Wait, Yura, you're
really going to go?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Now that's what I call
an active onmiyouji!
Let's go!
Shima!
Keikain!
-OK.
-Right.
-Maki!
Tori!
Come on!
-OK.
-Aww.
I guess I'm going to be
bombarded with questions again
at school.
-Rikuo.
-Oh!
Grandpa.
-I'd like to have a
few words with you.
-What is it?
-Is your injury healing well?
[gasp]
-Still, that Gyuki has
done the unforgivable.
After everything I've done for
him, how dare he draw his sword
and attack you?
-Huh?
-I'll expel him.
-No, don't!
-And after I do this, I'll
have him commit hara-kiri.
-No, Grandpa.
Please, wait a minute.
Gyuki was only thinking
about the clan.
-Well, then, Rikuo.
You shall be the one to
pass final judgment on all
of Gyuki's actions at the
clan's next General Assembly
as the next Supreme Commander.
-I understand, Grandpa.
[theme music]
-All right.
We need to hurry up now.
Everyone is going
to be here soon.
Oh!
[glass breaking]
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
-Lady Wakana, we
appreciate your help,
but we can handle the rest.
-No, that's all right.
I really enjoy helping out here.
-No, ma'am.
Really.
-This goes over here, right?
Oh!
[glass breaking]
-We don't have much
time, so please
don't give us any
more work to do.
[glass breaking]
-Whoops!
-I'm really worried.
What do we do if Master totally
bungles up today's General
Assembly?
Hmm?
-Look.
It's Snow Girl.
Hi.
-What?
Gozumaru and Mezumaru?
-You're so useless,
yet they still
keep you around as an attendant?
-What did you say to me?
More importantly, what
are you doing here?
-Haha.
The two of us are going
to be staying here
with the main family
for a little while.
-Ah!
-That's the way it
is for now, anyway.
So see you around, Snow Girl.
-Yeah.
See you.
-No way.
This can't be happening.
I won't accept it.
Master!
-The General Assembly of the
Nura clan is now in session.
-Oh.
Master Rikuo is in attendance.
-Yes.
It's been such a long time.
-Gyuki is here, too.
According to rumors, he turned
his sword on Master Rikuo.
-Then why has he come
to the General Assembly?
-There's probably going to
be some kind of judgment.
Let's just watch and
see what happens.
-This is impressive.
All of the big shots are here.
-Do you think Master
is going to be OK?
-What are you two doing there?
-Oh!
Lady Wakana.
-Well, it's a very important
day for Master Rikuo,
so we were just, um--
-At this assembly,
it will be decided
whether Master becomes
the third heir or not.
-Well, then!
I'm very glad that I
made red-bean rice today.
It's the perfect dish
for big celebrations.
-Huh.
-Celebration, huh?
-As usual, Lady Wakana is
so cheerful and optimistic
about everything.
-Yeah.
Nothing ever seems
to bring her down.
-She has faith in our master.
He is, after all, her son.
-Master Rikuo, why
can't you attend
this most important
meeting in your Yokai form?
-It's not like I can
switch back and forth
at the snap of my
fingers, you know?
-But Master, they just
won't take you seriously
if you walk in
looking like that.
-But there's nothing
I can do about it.
-What is the purpose of
this General Assembly?
If this meeting of the clan
is what I think it's for,
then this is hardly
the time for us
to be celebrating
with such a feast.
-What do you mean, Hitotsume?
-I say this for the
sake of the Nura clan.
It's time that we
settled things.
Once and for all.
-I fully agree.
So shall we begin?
I summoned you all here
today for one single purpose.
To strengthen the Nura clan.
To achieve this, I
plan to officially name
Rikuo Nura as the third heir
and next Supreme Commander.
-This is rather sudden,
don't you think?
-On the contrary.
I've been far too
idle until now.
The time has come for you
to take charge, Rikuo.
-But, Supreme Commander.
Before that, we must settle
this unfortunate issue
regarding Gyuki and his clan.
-Yes.
And it is my intention to
leave the final decision
on that to Rikuo.
-Isn't it a little too late to
place such high hopes on Master
Rikuo?
-Stand firm, Master Rikuo.
-Don't push me.
-I'm not!
-All right, Rikuo.
Tell us what your verdict is.
-OK.
On this most auspicious
day of the lunar calendar,
it is my pleasure to welcome
you to the Nura clan's General
Assembly.
I beg your pardon for addressing
you from this raised position.
I will accept the
responsibilities
as the third heir
of the Nura clan
and swear to live up
to its proud name.
However, I am a novice,
still in training
in the valiant
ways of the Yokai.
So if I misspeak, or am somehow
discourteous in my dealings,
I humbly ask for
your forgiveness.
Now, then.
Please allow me to explain
Gyuki's insurrection,
as it explains my decision.
As you may have
heard by now, Gyuki
did indeed cross swords with me.
Furthermore, it is
also true that he
used Kyuso, who had been
previously expelled,
and tried to
circulate a petition
to force my retirement.
-So it's true after all.
-What a fool.
Gyuki you won't get
off easily from this.
-However, it's indisputable that
he acted out of total devotion
to the Nura clan.
His actions resulted from
my apparent incompetence.
Thus, with regard
to this incident,
I judge Gyuki not guilty.
There is no sentence, and
I take full responsibility
for what happened.
-Ridiculous!
How could you say
something like that?
-It's my decision.
Do you question it?
-Yes.
Of course I do!
It's simple common
sense to punish
someone who commits treason.
-What Gyuki did was not treason.
-And what are you
basing that opinion on?
-As you are well
aware, the Nura clan
does not have any territory
west of Mount Nejireme which
Gyuki protects.
That mountain is
our clan's border.
It must be protected
at all costs.
In my mind, there is no one
but Gyuki who can do so.
Isn't that right, Gyuki?
-I would give my
life to protect it.
-That is why the Gyuki clan will
remain a part of our family.
OK.
I'm done.
Sorry to take up so much time.
-Grr.
-Hmm.
-Now, then.
We hereby decree
Master Rikuo to be
an official candidate
for the third heir.
And if no other
candidate appears
before his 13th birthday, the
coming of age for a Yokai,
Master Rikuo will
officially take over
and become the third Supreme
Commander of the Nura clan.
-Though a cloud of distrust
still hangs over the Nura clan,
Rikuo has embraced his destiny.
But is he truly ready
to lead the clan?
[theme music - in japanese]
-Would it be great if there
was a fashion Yokai who
could make anybody look cute?
-That sounds stupid.
Right, Kiyotsugu?
-No.
It's brilliant.
I'd love to meet one.
-Are you serious?
-Next time.