NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the night parade of 100
demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for
him-- the Lord of Pandemonium.
Nurarihyon.
[theme song]
MAN: The time has come when
we can finally leave this land
and ascend to the capital
to take our rightful place.
MAN: It is all because of
Inugamigyobu's beckoning.
He is, without doubt, destined
to rule over this world.
MAN: The seven
phantom travelers--
normally they are not
visible to the human eye.
But it is said they can be seen
if you peer between something--
like a cow's legs, for example.
Misfortune befalls
all who are unlucky
enough to encounter this group.
Such an encounter could
even result in death.
GIRL: Tamazuki and
the Seven Shadows.
-Hm?
-Karasu Tengu?
-Supreme Commander, where
have you run off to?
-Karasu Tengu.
Which way did he go?
-Master.
-Ao, Kubinashi.
-Did you see Lord Karasu Tengu
flying by the school just now?
-Yeah.
He looked upset.
-Do you know what's going on?
-No.
I mean, he flew right
by and didn't even seem
to notice us at all.
-But it must be
something very serious
for him to have
gone off like that.
-I'm gonna go talk to him.
-All right.
I'll go with you, master.
-Don't bother.
-Gozu.
Mezu.
-What are you guys doing here?
-Karasu is making
us work like slaves.
That old geezer of yours
went and disappeared,
so we gotta go out
and look for him now.
-What's the big deal?
Grandpa disappears all the time.
-Yes, that's true.
But Lord Hihi's unfortunate
demise just happened.
If something should happen
to the Supreme Commander
while he was out unattended--
-Kubinashi, cut it out.
Grandpa will be just fine.
-In any case, we'll help
Karasu look for the old geezer.
There's no need for you to
go wandering around too.
-That's right.
Especially when you're so
helpless during the daytime.
-I understand.
I'm counting on
you, Gozu and Mezu.
-Hm?
It's a big pain in the
ass, but what the heck.
Damn it all.
When you've got to
guard the main family,
you've really got no choice.
-Hey, Gozumaru, you're blushing.
-Uh-- would you just
shut up already?
-Ow!
-Come on, let's go.
-All right.
-What's with those two?
-I really don't know.
But they seem to be
quite dependable.
-Yeah.
And not only that,
Gyuki trust's them more
than anyone else in his clan.
I know I said he'd be all right,
but where'd Grandpa go, anyway?
Everyone's so worried.
-He's probably just
out walking around.
He'll stop somewhere
for some good food
and then make his
way back home again.
-I sure hope so.
-Hey, we're back.
-Oh, you two.
Where did you guys run off to?
I wasn't done talking yet.
-Huh?
We're sorry.
-They're always together.
-We ran into a mutual
friend that we haven't
seen in a really long
time, and we just
got to talking and stuff.
Isn't that right, Nura?
-Uh, yes, well-- ah, ah, Kana.
-Did you think a young girl
like me was easy to defeat?
-Supreme Commander,
did you see that?
-Not bad.
Behind you!
YURA (VOICEOVER): Dammit.
I failed to take out the boss.
-Lady Yura.
-I'm all right.
This is nothing.
YURA (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
When he attacked I got
some of his poison on me.
-Tanro, Rokuson!
If I could create an
opening for just an instant.
-You mustn't.
-Bukyoku--
-You cannot continue to control
four shikigami at the same
time.
Your body will not
hold out, Lady Yura.
-What are you saying?
Risking one's life
to exterminate Yokai
is the duty of an onmyouji.
Rokuson!
Tanro, no!
Bukyoku!
Enough!
Get back right now!
-Unfortunately, I can't
keep wasting my time playing
with you.
So long.
-Hold it!
Mr. Nura!
-Natto Kozo!
[laughter]
-I'm so sorry to
keep you waiting.
-Supreme Commander!
-Dammit!
-That girl won't be able to make
it up here for a little while.
You'd thought you'd
escape, but instead you've
been driven into a
corner, Nurarihyon.
-You hear that?
-I do.
It's the sound of
Muchi's poisonous wind.
-The present Nura
clan is vulnerable.
Take out its current leader and
it will completely fall apart.
And that will spell the end
of the Nura clan's night
parade of 100 demons.
-Tell me, Muchi, are you
the one who killed Hihi?
How regrettable.
He pledged loyalty to
me a long time ago,
and was one of the clan's
most respected veterans.
We would hang out
from time to time,
going to cafes for a cup of tea.
-He was right.
The Nura clan is so lax.
After all, their most
high-ranking officer
was nothing but a weakling!
It won't even take a
week to destroy you all!
-Do you know what you lack?
Elegance.
-Oh yeah?
You're running away from
my whip, but it's no use!
-Whoa.
-I'm trembling with excitement.
Now I get to have the honor
of killing a big-shot like you
with my own hands!
There's nowhere to run.
You will be sucked into
my whirlpool of wind
and be torn to shreds!
Mystic, eight balls of wind!
It's useless!
Even if you manage
to block my wind,
you can't escape
from this poison!
[cackling]
He bounced the wind back.
No.
There's no way he could do that.
He's gone?
Impossible.
I know I had him cornered.
He's here.
I know it.
He's walking in front of me.
And yet-- why-- why
can't I see where he is?
NURARIHYON: You cannot see as
long as you don't try to see.
No matter who you are, when
you encounter an existence that
is far greater than yourself
the fear begins to take over.
Your mind stops to
notice everything else.
So, even if you are
able to see, you
lose the ability to recognize.
That is my power.
Nurarihyons, meikyo shizui.
Like the calm surface of
water without any ripples.
So, how do you like
my style of fighting?
Quite elegant, eh?
-Damn you.
-Don't bother trying.
My dagger has cut you down,
and so you will not survive.
Tell me one thing
before you die.
Why would a Yokai from Shikoku
go through all this trouble
just to come after me?
-The wind hasn't died down yet.
-Mr. Nura!
-Huh?
Oh, young girl.
-Are you all right, Mr. Nura?
You're safe now.
I'm here to protect you.
Where's the Yokai?
Where'd it go?
-Huh?
Oh, that's thing.
It was here and
then it went away.
There's no need
to worry yourself.
Nothing really happened.
-It didn't?
-Oh, no, that's impossible!
Something must have happened
while it was up here!
I know something happened!
I know it!
-Oh, now, now.
I was hiding when
he stormed up here.
It went on a horrible, violent
rampage, and after a while
it just went away,
like the wind.
-Huh.
Like the wind?
-Yes, yes.
That's right.
And you see?
I'm not hurt at all.
I'm perfectly fine.
-Ugh.
I let another Yokai escape.
And it's all because I'm
so weak and hopeless.
I'm just no good as an onmyouji.
-That's not true.
You saved me.
Without your kind help I would
have most certainly died.
-Really?
You really do feel that way?
You're sure you're not hurt?
You're not sick or anything?
I'm so glad.
I'm glad that I
could protect you.
A very good man like you.
-I know you'll become a
fine onmyouji some day.
-Oh, I feel so much better!
And I'm getting hungry, too.
Say, Mr. Nura, how
about coming over
to my house for
some eggs over rice?
I'll even add some natto.
Mr. Nura?
-Oh, Supreme Commander!
I'm so glad you're OK.
-I'm happy to see that you
fared well yourself, Natto.
-Oh, no, never mind me.
We need to hurry
home right away.
Karasu will scold us
if he learns something
like this has happened to you.
-I'm not going home.
-Huh?
-There's something I want
to personally look into.
Tell them I won't be coming
home for a little while.
-What?
You can't do that!
-Or would you prefer
to come with me, Natto?
I could certainly
use some company.
-Wait!
Supreme Commander!
-Hey, Rikuo, is
something bothering you?
-Oh.
No, it's nothing.
-Are you sure?
I mean, you left the
club all of a sudden,
and then you've been really
quiet ever since you came back.
Something happen with Oikawa?
-No, you see, Kiyotsugu was
just rambling on and on today.
And I just got
tired of listening.
So I decided to take a break--
-Being a bodyguard is so boring.
-Shh.
-I have to say, the Yokai
knowledge he demonstrated today
was really impressive.
I wonder where he finds
those interesting facts.
-Considering how much you
dislike Yokai and all,
his stories must
be very unpleasant
for you to listen to, Ienaga.
-Oh, no, no.
Not at all.
I think it's really educational.
And-- how can I put it?
The more I learn about them,
the scarier they seem to me.
Yokai are supposed to be scary,
and that's perfectly normal.
And rather appealing.
-What the hell is
she talking about?
-Oh, man.
This is bad.
-Master--
-What is it, Tsurara?
You look mad.
-Spill it, master.
What exactly happened
between you and that-- that
girl the other night?
-Hey, take it easy.
Nothing happened.
Really.
-No, master.
A woman can sense these things.
That girl-- ever since that
day all she talks about
is your night form.
Maybe you haven't noticed, but
she's in L, in O, in V and E
with you!
-Huh?
Well, that's just crazy!
Besides, this isn't the time
to bring up stuff like that.
-You can't fool me anymore!
What happened that
night between you two?
Tell me the truth.
I want details!
-We didn't do anything.
-Why don't you just
come clean already?
-Ao!
Oh.
No, no.
This is-- girls?
-Oikawa, is your
house this way, too?
The same way as Rikuo?
-Yes it is, Ienaga.
Didn't you know that?
I mean, I thought you and
Nura were good old childhood
friends.
-They seem to be having fun.
-The master is quite
the heartbreaker.
-Yeah, like you should talk.
What's the matter, Kappa?
-What's this Yokai
aura I'm feeling?
-After it!
No one's here.
But I'm sure I sense
the presence of a Yokai.
-Hey, time out.
Why don't the two
of you calm down?
-Uh--
-Master!
-Oh, uh-- excuse me.
-Hello.
You're Rikuo Nura.
Isn't that right?
-Huh?
-And who the hell are you, kid?
-No, Ao.
I mean, uh, Kurata.
-Uh, Rikuo, do you know him?
-No, I don't.
-I guess I didn't need to ask.
I could tell just
by looking at you.
We have much in common.
Young and full of potential.
But most of all, we both
inherited the blood.
However, you had
everything handed to you
from the beginning, didn't you?
Whereas Ao sees
everything starting now.
-What do you mean
I had everything
from the very beginning?
-Am I wrong?
The way I see it you were
satisfied with your environment
and did nothing until
it was too late.
-Who are you?
What do you want?
-Just watch me.
I'll gather more fear than you
could ever hope to dream of.
-Gather fear?
-Wait, what do you mean?
-A girl on each arm, eh?
Must be great being
such a bigshot.
[scream]
-Kana!
-You creep.
-You let go of her.
-So, she's your precious
little human, I gather?
-Inugami.
That's enough fun
for the time being.
-Are you all right?
It's OK.
I'm fine.
What's that?
-Wha-- what's going on?
There-- there wasn't
anything like that
when I looked a minute ago.
-So you've arrived, my
seven phantom travelers.
Or should I say the officers
of the 88 demons of Shikoku?
We can do it.
We're going to take
over this land.
We're the ones who will rise.
NARRATOR: The seven
phantom travelers
have made themselves
known to the Nura clan.
What is their leader,
Inugamigyobu Tanuki Tamazuki's,
true goal?
[music playing]
GIRL: Here's a Nura clan quiz.
There are approximately 10,000
Yokai members in the Nura clan.
How many groups are
affiliated with the clan?
Find out the answer
in the next episode,
Lord Gyuki's Rebellion--
The Whole Story.