-You're--
-Forgive me for the other day.
I thought I'd come over
here to officially offer you
my greetings.
NARRATOR: This mysterious
group of beings
are known as the Seven Phantom
Travelers, Yokai originating
from the Shikoku region
of western Japan.
Normally they are not
visible to human eye,
but it is said they
can be seen if you
peer at them through the
space between two objects.
It is also said that
misfortune and maybe even death
would befall any who
encounters this group of Yokai.
-She'll make a sufficient foe!
NARRATOR: Inuhoo, a Yokai
that manipulates fire, and is
the self-appointed brains of
the Seven Phantom Travelers.
-You expect to
beat me in the sky?
Not in a million years!
-So are things busy
for you as usual?
NARRATOR: Kagibari
Onna, a female Yokai
who uses her needle hair
to take men captive.
-Your hair's a complete
and total mess, you know.
-How dare you, you
ridiculous cougar!
Passionate Woman-Killer
Needle Hell!
-My name is--
NARRATOR: Gangi Kozo wields
the power to control water.
He is formidable,
especially in the rain
where drug is at his
power's disposable.
Tearai-oni, he is the
strongest in all of Shikoku,
maybe even in all of Japan.
He has the ability to
grow in size at will.
his arch-enemy is the
Nura Clan strike team
leader, the mighty Aotabo.
Lord Sodemogi, as his
appearance may suggest,
he is physically weak, but he
should not be underestimated.
He is a fearful statue who has
the power to curse and kill
anyone who responds
to his calling.
-Praying to a rusty old deity
like this won't work, you know.
You should call my name instead.
I am Lord Sodemogi.
Call out my name now!
NARRATOR: Yosuzume, this Yokai's
but feather's steal light, so
that anything they
touch is plunged
into a deep,
disorienting darkness.
She is a silent Yokai who
never speaks or even utters
the smallest sound.
-So here you are, master.
I was worried about you.
I thought you came into
contact with Yosuzume.
-Yosuzume?
-That's right.
I've heard that the feather
of the Yokai known as Yosuzume
can slip into the eye through
the tiniest of openings,
and create total darkness
for whoever encounters it.
-A girl on each arm, eh?
NARRATOR: Inugami, a tortured
yet lonely stray dog Yokai
who turns hatred and
spite into strength.
-You creep.
NARRATOR: Inugami's story
is the most sad and tragic
of all the Yokai serving
Inugamigyoubu Tanuki Tamazuki.
And finally there is
Inugamigyoubu Tanuki Tamazuki
who leads the Seven
Phantom Travelers.
As the son of
Inugamigyoubu Tanuki
who has reigned over
the 88 Demons of Shikoku
for the last several
hundred years,
Tamazuki is a boy
who inherited much
of his father's great powers.
Though he was originally
named Tamazusa,
he decided to change
it to Tamazuki,
which means to covet
the throne, thereby
manifesting his
ambition, and setting
the stage for what was to come.
In days of old,
people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm, and led the night
parade of a hundred
demons was known
as the Supreme
Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium-- Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: The Seven Phantom
Travelers made their way
into eastern Japan, creeping
into the Nura Clan's territory
and headquarters to
fulfill Tamazuki's ambition
of conquering the entire nation.
-Oh.
Uh-- excuse me.
-Hello.
You're Rikuo Nura,
isn't that right?
-Uh, Rikuo, do you know him?
-No, I don't.
-I guess I didn't need to ask.
I could tell just
by looking at you,
we have much in common--
young and full of potential,
but most of all, we both
inherited the blood.
-You're Kana Ienaga, aren't you?
-Please, tell me.
-What?
-You know.
About him.
-Well he and I are much alike.
You see that, don't you?
He and I have a lot in common.
We've both been entrusted with
the responsibility and power
to rule over Yokai.
-You're wrong.
He isn't anything like you are.
NARRATOR: These
two girls continue
to be caught in the crossfire of
the fight between the Nura Clan
and the encroaching
88 Demons of Shikoku.
-Perfect timing.
Now you listen to me, Yokai.
I don't care what you
Yokai do among yourselves.
Go ahead and kill each
other all you want.
It'll make my job
that much easier.
However, I will not allow
you to harm any humans
while you fight your little war.
You remember that.
Here too.
NARRATOR: This
girl, Yura Keikain,
is a descendant of the
Keikain Clan of onmyoji,
Yokai exterminators from Kyoto.
Yura was sent to Ukiyoe Town
to hone her skills in Yokai
extermination, so she could
fulfill her future role
as head of the Keikain Clan.
-Last night?
-There's a good chance
that Yokai may still
be lurking around here.
So let's split up and search.
-OK.
Let's go that way.
-Come with us, Kana.
-OK.
-This whipping
wind is poisonous,
and if you sustain a deep
wound, it can kill you.
It's one of the Yokai found
in Shikoku named Muchi.
Mr. Nura, run away!
Hang on to this!
Rokuzan!
-A shikigami?
-Good.
I'm finally free
of my heavy burden.
NARRATOR: Kana Ienaga, Rikuo's
closest friend since childhood.
When the two of them were
young, Rikuo saved her life
from a an attack
by an evil Yokai.
For some reason, Kana has no
recollection of that event.
-You're still alive.
[chuckling]
-I'll kill everyone.
Sending all of you children
to the depths of hell
is what I enjoy doing.
-Master, we made it in time.
-Gagoze, a Yokai that
kills little children.
I'm glad everyone is OK.
If you're scared, you just
need to close your eyes.
Let it be known
to every Yokai-- I
shall be the Lord
of Pandemonium.
Follow me, and be part of
my night parade of a hundred
demons.
-This feels so good.
i haven't had a chance
to relax in a
bathtub for a while.
-It's rough being an
onmyoji, isn't it?
-Yeah.
And I'm still in training.
Ienaga, why didn't you run when
that suspicious looking guy
started talking to you?
-Because he reminded
me of another person.
But he turned out to
be nothing like him.
The person I know
is really scary,
but he makes me feel safe.
That guy Tamazuki
is very different.
He was really creepy.
Just thinking about him
makes me sick to my stomach.
I can't tell you
how awfully relieved
I was when you
told me that you'd
come over and spend
the night with me
-Ienaga, this person
you keep talking of,
is he the same Yokai
who saved us that day?
-Mhm.
-I knew it.
I better get out.
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
-Supreme Commander!
NARRATOR: This
dangerous showdown
between the young Yokai heirs
motivates Supreme Commander
Nurarihyon to seek out his old
rival, Inugamigyoubu Tanuki.
-It's been 300 years.
Inugamigyoubu Tanuki,
you've changed quite a bit.
-And you also, Supreme
Commander of the Nura Clan.
Instead of victory--
NARRATOR: 300 years ago,
the 88 Demons of Shikoku,
led by Inugamigyoubu Tanuki,
attacked a human castle.
The humans didn't seem to stand
a chance against the Yokai army
whose powers exceeded
all human capability.
However, the Tanuki
Yokai were massacred
by a single weapon used
by the humans, the legacy
of the conqueror,
the Devil's Blade.
But now, this sword lay
in the hands of Tamazuki.
-Lord Tamazuki awaits us.
-What's he doing?
-The Devil's Blade is
crying out for more.
What it wants is more blood,
more hatred to feed upon.
NARRATOR: And now
I must tell you
more about the tortured lonely
Yokai I mentioned earlier,
a follower of Tamazuki who did
his bidding, One of the Seven
Phantom Travelers, Inugami.
His heart was marred with
intense jealousy and hatred
for Rikuo.
INUGAMI (VOICEOVER):
So I tried desperately
to act like one of them.
INUGAMI: Um.
GIRL: What's with this guy?
He's scary.
GIRL: Ew. what a creep.
BOY: Man, he's annoying.
INUGAMI (VOICEOVER): But
they wouldn't accept me.
I spent my entire
life being ostracized.
All because I was born
a Yokai and not a human.
Back then I wasn't even aware of
that a world for Yokai existed.
NARRATOR: Now, are you
all familiar with the word
"koduku"?
If you put poisonous
insects in a single dish,
they will eat each other
until only one insect remains.
That last poisonous
insect is infused
with the hatred and curse
of the dead insects,
and the poison created
is known as koduku.
The koduku poison is a perfect
analogy to the Yokai Inugami.
-And he promised me
that he would take me
to a brand new world.
I want to see that world.
I'm very glad that I met him.
-Inugami, there's no one in this
world more loyalty than you.
[chuckling]
[theme music]
-Rikuo Nura, you like to
stick your nose into things,
don't you?
-Yeah.
I guess I do.
-All to save those humans?
How noble of you.
-What do you want?
-But it's useless.
Those humans are
going to become food
for the hungry Yokai
that live in this place.
Why?
Why is it that a weak, pathetic
and powerless little brat
like you gets to be accepted
by both humans and Yokai alike?
Why?
Answer me!
Why do you side with humans?
Humans are weak creatures
who fear and hate Yokai!
-You're wrong.
Not all human hate Yokai.
[chuckling]
-Well this is the
last day you'll ever
be able to act so righteous.
Why would you do this?
Why?
Why do you have to put
me through all this crap?
-It's quite simple.
I want to see how
strong you are.
-How strong?
I'm not strong at all.
TAMAZUKI: Then do
you want to die?
-There are no
humans in this world
who don't detest Yokai
and find us disgusting.
Humans, those damn humans.
Each and every one
of them treated
me like I was some
kind of monster!
I'm gonna kill him, and complete
Tamazuki's collection of fear.
Our time has finally come!
Now take me to the
new Yokai world.
I swear I will follow
you until the very end!
You are the only one fit to
take control of this world.
Shall i prove it to them?
Give me the order, and I'll
gladly bring you his head.
We must show that damn Nura
Clan the vast difference
between Rikuo Nura
and you, Tamazuki.
Come on, Tamazuki.
Let me be your thing,
so I can tear him apart.
Tamazuki, what's the matter?
Why are you doing this to me?
Tamazuki?
Why?
TAMAZUKI: I'm grateful to you.
With your strength, the Devil's
Blade will attain perfection.
You were a truly
loyal dog to me.
-But-- but I-- I
did it all for you.
-I feel it-- this power.
This is fear!
NARRATOR: Tamazuki, this
fear you keep harping about,
tell me.
Are we supposed to feel
it emanating from you?
No one's gonna follow
a guy who bears
the corpses of his comrades.
-That is without a doubt a
flurry of cherry blossoms.
-Shut the hell up!
What?
I just cut you down, so how
can you still be standing?
-Kyoka Suigetsu.
TAMAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Another
one of Nurarihyon's techniques?
It doesn't matter.
I am the one who surpassed my
father, Inugamigyoubu Tanuki!
-It's not your father
you need to surpass.
The only person you need to
overcome here is yourself!
[scream]
-Tamazuki!
-No!
My hundred demons,
they're leaving me!
-Tamazuki.
-My powers are fading.
NARRATOR: During the battle,
Inugami lost his life,
and Tamazuki's dream
of conquering all Japan
finally came to an ignoble end.
[barking]
NARRATOR: Might this puppy be
the reincarnation of Inugami?
Of course, nobody can know for
certain one way or another.
Perhaps it's just
another stray dog.
But it seems that Tamazuki
saw something in him.
-I'm never going
to spoil, you know.
[barking]
[theme music]