NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and lead the Night Parade
to 100 Demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
A Yokai that attacks and
devours lost travelers
lives up here on this mountain.
Its original name was Mt.
Nejireme.
NARRATOR: A beautiful mountain
where plum blossoms dance,
but it is actually
home to menacing Yokai.
-The Yokai who lives on Mt.
Nejireme is him.
It's Gyuki.
NARRATOR: Was it a trap,
or sheer coincidence
that they had wandered onto
the territory of Gyuki,
an officer of the Nura clan?
An ominous wind blows
across the eerie slopes
of the evil mountain.
GIRL (VOICEOVER): A Trap Is
Set On The Evil Mountain.
GIRL: Hey, are you
sure it's safe up here?
GIRL: I don't know, but
one thing is certain.
It's no ordinary mountain.
BOY: Are you serious?
-It's creepy!
-I wanna go home!
[laughter]
-Aw, come on.
Why are you guys so freaked out?
It's finally starting to
feel like a real Yokai tour!
-But Kiyotsugu--
-A huge claw like that
would kill us all.
-Yeah, and we'd all be devoured!
-Calm down, you two.
All right?
-But we're scared!
-The Gyuki clan, the most
militant faction of our clan.
There's a chance they
may attack the master
without knowing who he is.
After all, he's still
in his day form.
Without Ao here, things
could get really ugly.
If it does, I must
protect master.
-Oikawa is staring
at Rikuo agian.
Kyotsugu, I think Maki and
Torii are absolutely right.
We should turn around
right now and go home.
-Now, let's get out of here!
-Hey, hold on!
Even if we leave
the mountain now,
there won't be
any buses running.
-Aw.
-There's an exclusive
Japanese inn just up ahead
that Professor Adashibara
reserved for us.
A relaxing hot spring and a
delicious multi course meal
await us there!
Naturally, all costs will
be covered by yours truly,
all right?
-Hot spring?
-A multi course meal?
-For free?
That's so cool!
-No, listen!
It's better we all go home!
[laughter]
-The story of Gyuki is no
more than a simple legend,
and those big claws you all
saw were probably fake, anyway.
-Yes, but--
-Besides, the inn
is fully equipped
with a security
system against Yokai.
There's nothing to
be worried about.
-Security?
Against Yokai?
-It's has not only that.
If, by chance, we are
attacked while we're there,
we have Yura Keikain,
our very own Onmioji,
to step in and protect us.
Isn't that right?
-Yeah.
-Hey, you're right!
-I will redeem my
honor as Onmyoji.
Better separate my Shikigami
from my old receipts.
No, this coupon expires soon!
-All right, then, if there
are no more objections,
let's continue with the
Keiyojuji Paranormal Patrol
field trip!
TOGETHER: Yay!
We're continuing on!
-Well, I guess
I'll be going now.
I hope you all enjoy yourselves.
Goodbye.
-Please join us, professor.
We wanna hear more of
your great Yokai stories.
-No, no.
By job here is done.
I really have to get going.
Oh yes.
It's almost sundown.
Once the mountain grows dark,
you must not go outside.
-Well.
That went smoothly.
-Huh?
Who could that be?
-Damn it all.
I got separated
from master Rikuo.
Huh?
Oh.
Excuse me, do you know
the way to [inaudible]?
-Oh, it's, uh--
-Thank you very much.
-Don't mention it.
Take care.
Heh, heh, heh.
-Yes.
Nicely done.
-What am I doing here like this?
Huh?
-You fooled them well, Mezumaru
-Yeah, but it wasn't
easy, Gozumaru.
-So, what do we do now?
-First, we'll separate
them all, and then I'll
find and kill Rikuo's aid.
-You can leave all the weaklings
to me, and I'll get rid of them
quickly.
-The night of the
full moon end storm.
The perfect time to hunt
for a leader's head.
-Good evening.
We are honored to
welcome you to Togyobo.
-Good evening to you.
We're glad to be here.
-Thanks for having us!
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): This
place feels sorta weird.
-What's the matter, Rikuo?
Is something wrong?
-Uh, no, no.
Nothing at all.
It's a very nice
place, isn't it?
-It is.
It looks like a really elegant
and well established inn.
-A talisman to ward off Yokai.
You see?
The professor was right.
The Yokai security
here is perfect.
-Ah!
-Wait.
That's the talisman?
KIYOTSUGU: Aren't
you glad we came?
A chance to stay in an exclusive
inn like this is so rare!
And it's all thanks to Professor
Adashibara's connections.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): I can't
let everyone get scared.
I have to act natural, and
stay on alert for danger.
-Um, can we go in the
hot springs right away?
-Oh yes.
There's a natural outdoor bath
where you and your friends
can soak any time you wish.
-Yahoo!
-Let's go straight
to the outdoor bath!
-Outdoor bath?
-Wow.
How cool.
-Kana, don't lag behind.
-Where's Oikawa and Yura?
-They're-- Oh, they
were just here.
-Yuki Onna soaking in hot
water is like suicide.
-The girls are probably
enjoying the hot spring
right around now.
-That's right, Kiyotsugu.
-Now's our chance.
-You bet.
Let's go out and
do it right now.
If we time it right, I'll be
able to see Oikawa's beauty!
-OK, Shima, time
for us to get going!
-Right.
We're gonna go look for Yokai!
-Huh?
-Uh, we're looking for Yokai?
KIYOTSUGU: Remember Professor
Adashibara's last words?
He said not to go out once
the mountain grows dark,
meaning that's
when Yokai appear!
Come on, Shima.
Let's go!
-No, wait!
You shouldn't go
out there right now.
You guys aren't taking
the Yokai seriously.
There really some Yokai
that attack humans.
-Nura?
-What the heck are
you saying, Nura?
What would you know
about Yokai anyway?
Don't try to stop us.
Unlike you, I'm
totally committed
to my search for Yokai!
-If you insist on
going, I'm coming too.
-It's too dangerous with
just the two of you.
-Well, if you are
going, then I'm going.
-Tsurara.
-Oikawa.
Right.
Let's go.
-Finally, we'll get to
encounter some Yokai!
I'm so excited.
-Hm?
-This really is heavenly.
-This hot spring is the best.
-Yura and Tsurara should
be here bathing with us.
Don't you think?
-Yeah, they're missing out.
KANA (VOICEOVER): Oikawa.
Does she like Rikuo?
Why am I so concerned?
It's none of my business.
Maybe Oikawa isn't here
with us because she's
meeting up with Rikuo.
Oh, stupid me.
Why do I care, anyway?
-Kana.
Hey, Kana.
What's the matter with you?
-Well, I, um-- I'm getting out.
-So soon?
-You should soak
a little longer.
Hey!
-Yes.
It's almost time for us to
have our dinner, isn't it?
All right, everyone.
Let's go down there
and fill our bellies.
KANA (VOICEOVER):
They must be together.
I just wanna confirm.
That's all I wanna do.
KIYOTSUGU: All right!
Here we go!
Kiyojuji Paranormal
Patrol, move out!
Ha ha ha!
LORD GYUKI: We'll lure
Rikuo Nura to this mountain.
-Lord Gyuki, does
mean you're finally--
-Yes.
-Mezumar, are you
trembling there?
-No.
I'm just excited.
I have absolutely no objections
to your plan, my Lord Gyuki.
Order me, and I
shall gladly obey.
-And you, Gozumaru?
-To defy the main family
is against our code,
but our ultimate
duty is to carry out
your orders, Lord Gyuki.
We pledged our loyalty to you.
We shall not fail in
our service to you,
if this is the decision
you've reached, Lord Gyuki.
-Yes, it is.
After a very long and
careful deliberation.
MAN: If Rikuo Nura dies on Mt.
Nejireme, it will
be obvious that it
was the doing of the Gyuki clan.
There will be no
turning back for us.
But if the decision
Lord Gyuki has reached
is to go through with
this plan, then I
shall accompany my lord
until the very end.
-This place is strange.
And there doesn't seem
to be any other guests.
-Hey, what's the matter?
Don't tell me it's
a peeping Tom.
I'm gonna kill those guys.
Hey, you perverts.
Are you peeking out there--
[scream]
-Don't come any closer!
[laughing]
-You fools.
I put up that talisman myself.
-Huh?
-This is Lord Gyuki's
territory, so that's here
to ward off Yokai
from other clans.
-You mean this Yokai security
was made by you guys?
-Yeah, that's right.
So don't peel it off!
-Rokuson!
-A Shinigami?
-It's Yura!
-You Yokai have a lot
of nerve attacking girls
who are in the
middle of bathing!
KIYOTSUGU: Look!
Down there is a Yokai
spot, the Ushigakure Cave!
Legend has it that
long ago, a priest who
was being attacked
by a group of Yokai
took refuge in this very place.
I mean, this is a
truly historical spot!
Shima, go down there.
-Not a chance.
-Watch out, Master!
Oh, it's just a racoon dog.
-What a loser.
And he's the grandson
of Nurarihyon?
-All right, now, there are other
Yokai spots we can explore.
-Nura, you're pretty clumsy,
so be careful where you walk.
-Ah!
Master Rikuo, it's a trap!
A trap!
Run away, run away!
-It's just a spiderweb.
-Oh.
All right.
This is the Yokai spot
known as the one-eyed pine!
Let's pass through
one at a time.
-I'll go first.
-Wait a minute, I wanna
go through it first.
I wanna make sure it's
safe and sound before I
let anyone else try it.
-Hey.
What exactly are you up to?
I'm just trying to
protect you, Master.
I mean, that is my
sworn duty, after all.
-Well, that's really nice of
you, but you don't have to.
-What?
What are you talking about?
Of course I do.
At present, you are
in your human form,
we're in a dangerous place,
and I don't know where Ao is.
And that means right now,
I'm the only aid here
to protect you, sir.
-Master.
Master!
Where are you, Master?
Seriously.
Where in the hell am I?
-Look.
Never mind me.
Think about how we can
protect those two over there.
KIYOTSUGU: See that
up there, Shima?
RIKUO: I'll be too late
if something happens.
-So she's his closest aid, huh?
Grandson of Nurarihyon, Instead
of worrying about others,
worry about yourself.
Although it's far too late now.
[chanting]
-Hey, Shima, which
direction do you
think we should go
to see some Yokai?
-I think we should go left
through that clearing.
-Well, I think we go right.
-I see.
-Huh?
Hey, you two.
Wait!
-Master!
-This is weird.
Something's wrong here.
Hey!
Tsurara!
Go after Shima!
-Master!
I have protect Master Rikuo.
But Master's orders
to me are absolute.
I don't know what to do.
-Rikuo.
Where did you go?
-Don't falter.
You have to get them!
What?
-Something is definitely wrong.
This place.
No, this entire mountain is--
-Look, Shima, it's
a pretty Yokai.
-Hey, you're right.
-Tsurara.
-It's frozen.
-Who are you?
Do you belong to the Gyuki clan?
-So what if I do?
-I warn you.
Don't do anything stupid.
Now, do you have
any idea who I am?
-I see.
You're Yuki Onna.
-If you know, then
put away your sword,
and you will not be
blamed for any of this.
[snickering]
-What's funny?
You know, if I were to
you, I'd cut the laughing.
You don't seem to realize
who you're messing with.
Who do you think
my master is, huh?
-Why don't you just
shut your damn mouth?
Don't underestimate our clan.
We're putting our lives
on the line for this.
-You mean Lord Gyuki sent
you to kill Master Rikuo?
-The ever discreet Lord
Gyuki planned everything,
except that.
-Cursed Blizzard!
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Master-- he's in danger.
I am supposed to protect him.
-Die!
-Tsurara!
-No, Master, run away!
-You're too late!
-Listen, you bastard.
This woman serves
me, Rikuo Nura,
the Nura clan's third heir.
She's my subordinate.
If you attacked her knowing
that, I will kill you.
-Master.
NARRATOR: Two swords
gleam in the darkness.
A sharp hunger for blood
cuts through a frozen moment.
[theme music]
KIYOTSUGU: I got it, Shima!
SHIMA: Got what?
KIYOTSUGU: The name of the Yokai
that I'll eventually discover.
SHIMA: And that name is?
KIYOTSUGU: The Nurara Kiyojuji
Itonmoma Nurakame Kiyotsugu
Special!
NARRATOR: Next
time, darkness moves
on the night of the new moon.