NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
Demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for
him-- the Lord of Pandemonium,
Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
Ah.
What are you up to, master?
-Yuki Onna.
I was looking at the moon.
Isn't it pretty?
-Yes, it is.
-You know, I wish every day was
quiet and peaceful like this.
-It's the perfect night
to go scare people!
-Uh, well-- yeah, it is.
NARRATOR: Rikuo has demonstrated
his strong resolve and kindness
by forgiving Yuki's treason.
However, unbeknownst
to Rikuo, ominous winds
were already beginning to sir
and blow in from the west.
GIRL: Eating The Fruit From
Beyond The Evil Mirror.
[laughter]
-Huh?
MALE VOICE: Kana.
Kana.
Let's play again sometime.
-I had that terrible
dream again.
The same dream I've been having
since I was six years old.
It's my birthday, and I had
to wake up feeling like this.
Huh?
KANA (VOICEOVER): I'm so sleepy.
I didn't sleep well because
of that creepy dream.
MALE VOICE: Kana.
You're still six years old.
When you're older,
let's play again.
I promise, I'll come
and get you on your--
KANA (VOICEOVER): Promise?
What promise?
I can't remember.
[whistle]
-Nice, Shima!
-Way to go, Japan's under
14 soccer representative.
-Go!
Go!
-Thanks a lot for
helping out, Aotabo.
I mean, Kurata.
-No problem.
This is nothing.
-Hooray!
Hooray!
Faster!
-You can stop that now, Tsurara.
-You've got it wrong.
One more time.
Don't be embarrassed.
The uho stuff will help
protect you from Yokai.
This one's designed for
beginnings like yourself.
-Why on earth do we have to--
-Learn how to do something
as weird as this?
-It's for your own good.
Do you wanna be assaulted
in the nude again?
[groaning]
KANA (VOICEOVER): What was it?
The promise.
-Come on.
You should learn it too, Ienaga.
-Huh?
Wait.
-In fact, you're
the one who needs
to learn it more than
anyone else here.
'Cause you always
seem to encounter
Yokai wherever you go.
Now, copy me.
MAN: I see you're
all working hard!
-That's not ninpo.
-Practicing Onmyoji's self
defense jutsu under blue skies,
oh, the magnificent sight of
energetic youth in action!
All right!
I've got new Yokai
encounter stories to share.
GIRLS: Oh, boy.
-But before all that--
-What is it?
-Ienaga, today is the happy day
you were born into this world.
Happy birthday.
-Wow, it's your birthday?
-Oh, happy birthday.
-But you didn't have to.
-Come on, Ienaga,
no need to feel shy.
You're part of this group.
I want you to accept it.
-Well then, thank you.
-Well, open it.
I wanna see what you got.
-Wow, that box.
It's a fancy brand!
-Uh-- is that a voodoo doll?
-What is this thing?
-It's a little doll
of you in Yokai form!
What do you think?
It is amazingly cute, isn't it?
-Yuck!
Who'd want that?
-What?
But I had this doll made
by a famous designer.
-What a big waste
of their talent.
-Thank you for the
gift, Kyotsugu.
Excuse me, I have to go now.
-Huh?
Aren't you going to stay
for our Yokai discussion?
-I'm sorry I'm
really sleepy today.
-There.
I'm all done.
I just have to return
these to the classroom.
You guys can go on ahead.
-But master--
-You're in charge of
making dinner, right?
Head on back to the house.
You don't have to
worry about me.
-Yeah.
Just leave it to me.
I'll take care of the master.
-Kay.
Well, I guess I'll be
going on home, then.
Just don't stay
out too late, OK?
-Don't worry.
I won't.
-Please hurry home!
All right?
KANA: It's sweet how
he brought me a gift,
but this is kind of-- well--
KIYOTSUGU (VOICEOVER):
Happy birthday!
MALE VOICE: On your
birthday, I'll come for you.
-I'd better hurry home.
-Have any of you heard the
story of the purple mirror?
-Uh-uh.
What is it about?
-It's about the
Yokai Ungaikyo, also
known as the purple mirror, the
mirror that reveals all demons.
It it said that if you
look into this mirror,
you will be killed on
your 13th birthday.
KANA (VOICEOVER):
I don't remember
the station being this far away.
GIRL: Killed?
Why on the 13th birthday?
-In the Yokai world,
you're considered an adult
as soon as you
turn 13 years old.
-Oh.
That makes sense.
-So once you become an
adult, it kills you?
-Yes.
Like eating a piece
of ripe fruit.
-Yeah, well we're not fruit, OK?
-Sorry I'm late.
KIYOTSUGU: Hey, Nura!
What took you?
-I was cleanup monitor today.
Say, where's Kana?
[bells]
-Found you.
A very happy 13th
birthday to you.
As I promised, I've
come for you, Kana.
-No!
-Let's play, Kana.
Let's pick up where we
left off seven years ago.
-I don't know what
you're talking about!
What's happening?
It's like from my dream.
But why?
How?
-A game of tag?
You can't escape me, Kana.
-I know.
I'll do uho.
Oh, no!
I forgot how to do it!
[laughter]
-Kana!
-No!
The school?
Why?
-A lovely game of tag,
inside the mirror.
[scream]
KANA: How did I get here?
I was walking-- no, running
towards the train station.
And yet, somehow I'm
back here at the school.
A purple mirror?
-Kana, you're still
six years old.
When you're older,
let's play again.
I promise, Kana.
I'll come and get you on the
day of your 13th birthday.
-I remember!
-Kana, this room
doesn't have a mirror.
It's cramped.
So cramped!
RIKUO: Ungaikyo?
KIYOTSUGU: You know about it?
-Mm-mm.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
I've never heard of it.
Maybe it's a rogue Yokai that
was expelled from another clan.
So anyway, you were saying that
it's Kana's birthday today?
-That's right.
I just gave her a
great birthday present.
I have one just like it, myself.
-That's really gross.
-That's so rude!
It's a very cute doll
of me as a Yokai.
But that's not all.
-Gah.
I can't get out!
-No!
Mirrors.
He comes out through mirrors.
I have to run!
[buzzing] What's that?
What's going on?
KIYOTSUGU: Hello!
Can you hear me?
-Kiyotsugu?
[laughter]
-Did I surprise you?
That cute Yokai doll
I gave you today
has a cellphone built into it.
It's how the Kiyojuji paranormal
patrol will communicate.
-Are you there?
-Ah!
Help!
Help me!
I'm being attacked by a monster
A horrible mirror monster!
-Ienaga!
-A mirror monster?
-You mean-- Kana, where are you?
-In one of the boys
restrooms on campus.
-Found you!
Ha ha ha ha!
KIYOTSUGU: Hello?
Hello?
Ienaga!
-Hurry!
We have to find her!
-All right.
Which boys restroom?
-Kiyotsugu, you go that way.
I'll look this way.
-Ah--
-She's not here.
-You in here?
-Kiyotsugu!
Hey, wait, I'm here!
Why can't you see me?
-She's not here, either.
-No one will come for you.
No one.
Let's play.
Kana!
[scream]
RIKUO: Kana!
-Rikuo!
-How can he see us in here?
This place is just
for me and Kana!
-No!
-Kana!
-I'm-- being pulled in!
[laughter]
-No!
It's you again.
-Never lay a hand on a
woman in my territory.
-Who are you?
A Yokai?
Don't get in my way!
[laughter] How's this?
I bet you can't tell
which one is me!
-You fool.
Since I don't know, I'll just
destroy all of you at once.
[groan]
-Th-- thank you.
Um--
KIYOTSUGU: Ienaga!
-Did you find her?
-No, not yet.
-Damn, where the
heck could she be?
KANA: Everyone!
-Huh?
-Ienaga!
-Where's the Yokai?
-Oh, sorry.
Um, I, uh, I made a mistake.
I kind of dozed off, and thought
this doll was a real Yokai.
So everything's fine, really.
See you tomorow.
-Huh?
-Hey!
Wait!
Tell me, who are you?
You came when that
rat Yokai trapped us,
and then once again
on our field trip.
And now-- it seems wherever
Rikuo is, you appear.
Are you-- could
you be-- don't go.
Can you stay with
me a little longer?
Please tell me more
about yourself.
-So, you don't mind?
Being scared?
This way.
Is something wrong?
Are you too scared?
-Mm-mm.
I'm not because I'm here.
With you.
-After you.
-Um, where are we?
-You want to know
more about me, right?
I'll show you everything
you want to know.
-Uh, well, OK.
-Good evening!
Welcome to our
place, Bakenekoya,
the best Yokai
restaurant there is.
-Come on in!
-Hey, there.
-Master.
-You've got quite a place here.
Looks like business is good.
-You can count on me.
I promise, I'll
never screw up again.
Say, master, isn't she
the same human girl
who was kidnapped by Kyuso?
You sure it's OK to bring
her to a place like this?
-Say, Ryota Neko, I
need a favor from you.
-There's Yokai everywhere.
-You're such a sly dog,
aren't you, master?
-Look at the cute
lover he brought today.
-Lover?
GIRL: I'm so jealous.
KANA (VOICEOVER): They're
calling him master.
So he really is a Yokai.
-Well, here you go.
So, what might your name be?
-Kana.
-How old are you?
I'm 12.
Actually, I'm 13 today.
WAITER: It's your birthday?
Hey, that's great!
-So you just became
an adult today?
I think that's wonderful!
-I'm sure you'll make
a terrific Yokai.
-So what kind of Yokai are you?
-Um, I--
-If they find out
that you're human,
they might decide to eat you.
-Master--
-Come on, don't
leave us hanging.
-Well, um-- you see--
KANA (VOICEOVER): What'll I do?
Would they really eat me?
-A mirror!
Is-- this for me?
-It's your birthday.
So just take it.
-Thank you.
I love it.
GIRL: Oh!
This doll is so cute.
Where do they sell these?
-Oh, well, that's--
-Let me see it.
-Oh, so cute!
-I want one, too.
KANA (VOICEOVER): So this is
what the Yokai world is like.
It's now how I imagined it.
-Oh.
So cute.
Is this little
child a Yokai, too?
-Yeah.
He's tasty.
-Don't say that!
-Wow, there are so
many kinds of Yokai.
-My, my.
I'm stuffed.
The old lady at the sweet
shop sure can cook up a storm.
Eh?
-I'm so worried
about the master.
I can't believe how
late he's staying out.
You said, leave it to me,
I'll take care of the master.
How could you just
lose him like that?
[groan]
-Ow!
-Can I have another glass
of catnip juice, please?
-Well, I'm very glad she had
a good time here tonight.
-Yeah.
Thanks for the food.
-Hm.
So, Rikuo didn't come
home until morning?
-No.
It seems he didn't.
[laughter]
-The boy is becoming
quite busy, eh?
-Yes.
I suppose you're right, Father.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Oh,
what was I thinking?
I shouldn't have done
what I did last night.
-Pardon me.
Mater, what were you doing
until so early this morning?
-Huh?
Well, um, you see--
KANA: Morning.
-Oh.
Kana.
Sorry about last night.
I mean--
-Last night!
-Um, say, Rikuo-- I want
to ask you something.
Come on.
-What happened?
-So Kana, you wanted
to ask me something?
-I've been going over
and over everything
that's been happening up to now.
And it seems whenever
you're there, he's there.
Even yesterday.
Rikuo, could it be
that he and you--
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
She knows?
-Are friends with each other?
-Ah?
Huh?
-Please, tell me more about him.
-I don't understand.
Why do you want to know?
-Well, does it really matter?
It's got nothing to do with you.
[screaming]
-Hm.
[humming]
-Oh, sorry.
We won't be open for a while.
Ah!
-What was that sound?
It was awfully loud.
Saburo Neko?
What happened to you?
-Huh?
Must be from that
last gust of wind.
Anyway, I'm fine.
My clothes just got
a little torn up.
-I see.
-I'm going to go change.
MAN: A little torn up?
They're so clueless.
-The rumors were right.
The Nura clan is a
bunch of softies.
Good thing we came
to spy on them.
-Ukiyoe Town.
The headquarters
of the Nura clan.
They don't realize their
days are numbered here.
They've got a week at most.
[laughter]
[theme music]
AOTABO: The button on the
school uniform is killing me.
TSURARA: Stop
being so silly, Ao.
You have that thing
unbuttoned all the time.
AOTABO: Not as silly
as that scarf of yours.
RIKUO: Come on, you guys.
Next time, The Vanguard
Wind Blows From The West.