NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm, and led the night
parade of a hundred
demons was known
as the Supreme
Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium-- Nurarihyon.
[theme music] had
TAMAZUKI: So Rikuo
Nura appeared.
-Yes, and he's no ordinary brat.
-I didn't expect to
hear you say that.
It just makes all
of us coming here
to Ukiyoe Town that much
more worthwhile, however,
he doesn't have a clue that he's
already imprisoned in my trap,
and is being completely
manipulated by me.
-I wonder when the stupid
little brat will realize it?
-When he finally does,
it'll be way too late.
-I hope that all of
you will continue
to show your support for me.
I'm counting on you.
-Yes, of course.
-We will gladly give our
lives to carry out your order.
That will give rise to the
dawn of the Shikoku Yokai.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): "The
Sublime Spirit Burns Crimson.
-Do you really think
that these interlopers
are attempting to
destroy the Nura Clan?
-Our clansmen are being
attacked one after another.
Isn't that the
obvious conclusion?
-No.
Think about it for a moment.
Would the destruction
of the Nura Clan
really benefit
the Shikoku Yokai?
-Hm.
If they seriously
considered their future,
they would want to rule
over us, and increase
their military power.
KARASU: Then what is the true
aim of these Shikoku Yokai?
-I don't know.
-It's dawn.
-Gyuki is right.
If they intended to
destroy the Nura Clan,
they would have made
an all out attack.
The fact that they haven't means
they're after something else.
I have to settle
this before Kana
and everyone else
are put in danger.
-That was a really close call.
-Yeah.
I'm gonna get that
middle aged broad.
I'll totally pulverize
her next time we meet.
-Well thank goodness master
showed up and saved you.
KEJORO: No kidding.
Who would've imagined
that Master Rikuo would
come to my rescue.
I was so surprised
when he arrived.
I suppose that this means he
does cherish me after all.
He was so handsome and dashing.
-Oh.
Sorry about that.
Now try not to be quite
so reckless from now on.
You're not quite as
young as you used to be.
[humming]
-Huh?
KIYOTSUGU: Kiyojuji
Paranormal Patrol assemble!
Take a look at this!
-What is that?
-A map of Ukiyoe Town?
-What do all those
X marks on it mean?
-That's an excellent
question, Shima!
What you see here is
a compilation of data
I came up with using my
intelligence network.
It shows all the
shrines in Ukiyoe Town,
including the small
ones that have
been destroyed by
some unknown vandal.
-Huh?
Did you just say they've
all been destroyed?
-Yes.
There's been a rash of
these incidents in town.
-So what about it?
KIYOTSUGU: That's a
silly question, Ienaga.
This is undoubtedly
the work of Yokai.
-No.
It's probably a
drunk of something.
-The Kiyojuji Paranormal Patrol
will get to the bottom of this
by finding the Yokai responsible
for this blatant vandalism!
We begin now!
Kiyojuji Patrol, move out!
-Right.
-What?
KIYOTSUGU: OK.
Let's go.
SHIMA:You mean
right this instant?
KIYOTSUGU: Of
course, this instant.
-Wait a minute.
Don't leave here.
It's dangerous outside.
-What'll we do?
-I have to go protect them.
-By yourself?
-No.
Sanba Garasu, Aotabo.
-At your service, Master Rikuo.
-I need an escort.
-Oh.
Are you going out?
-Yes.
For Kiyojuji Patrol work!
-I see.
Please be careful out there.
-Thank you, Mrs. Nura!
-Wait.
We're coming with you.
-The clan is facing
a serious crisis,
and Rikuo is going
out with his friends?
How irresponsible.
-Here to.
What exactly is
happening to Ukiyoe Town?
-Look, look, look!
-Kiyotsugu?
-This shrine was perfectly
fine yesterday afternoon.
All this damage was
done last night.
-Last night?
-There's a good chance
that Yokai may still
be lurking around here, so
let's split up and search.
SAORI: OK.
NATSUMI: Let's go that way.
SAORI: Mhm, Come with us, Kana.
KANA: OK.
KIYOTSUGU: C'mon.
Let's go, Shima.
I'm gonna make sure I
encounter a Yokai today!
-Oikawa.
-I suppose there's really
no need to hide from them.
-Let's start from here.
-OK.
-The shrine is
starting to crumble.
-And there are no signs
of the local deity.
I'd say--
-It's the work of some Yokai.
-Wait a minute.
What are they whispering about?
-Look at this cloth.
What do you think?
-A piece torn from a kimono?
-Are they kissing in
a place like this?
Those two have something going?
I can't see from this side.
-So do you think that this is
the work of the Shikoku Yokai?
-I'm confused.
I thought that Nura
and Ienaga were dating.
He's two-timing?!
-Oh no, master.
What if she heard
what we were saying?
-Wha-- what do we do?
-Why if it isn't Yura.
-Hi, Yura.
Is your injury feeling better?
-Nura.
-Uh-- yes?
-He who runs after two
hares will catch neither.
-What?
-Don't underestimate rabbits.
-Uh.
-What's the matter with Yura?
-I don't know.
-Oh.
Um-- here.
-Hm?
Wow!
Excellent job, Nura!
You found a clue to
the Yokai who did this!
-I don't if it's a clue or not.
-We'll leave it to my
intelligence network
to find out.
We are going to check
this clue out thoroughly.
[laughter]
NARRATOR: Meanwhile, over
in the Shikoku mountains.
-Something is odd.
-What?
Again?
What is it that's bothering
you so much about this place?
I don't sense anything
odd around here at all.
-It stinks.
I've been on guard
here for 200 years,
but I've never smelled
anything like this stench.
Wait a minute.
It's natto.
There shouldn't be a smell
like this anywhere around here.
-This is an odd place after all.
I can't believe they
don't have natto beans.
-That's not what I meant when
I said something's odd, Natto.
This area used be much
more dangerous than this.
-It was?
-Outsiders can't pass.
-Ow.
-Get back here you, brat.
-Wait for me, Supreme Commander!
-You can't hide from me.
I know this place
much better than you
-Supreme Commander!
-It's been 300 years,
Inugamigyoubu Tanuki.
You've changed quite a bit.
-And you also, Supreme
Commander of the Nura Clan.
-What is this.
There's so many.
-It seems there are
less than before.
-Oh.
Is that right?
-Long ago, there
were 108 of these.
-Where are we?
-This is the home of the kingpin
of the Shikoku's Yokai's clans,
the headquarters of the 88
Demons of the Shikoku Yamaguchi
Holy Shrine.
Isn't that so?
-Yes.
-Hey, boss.
Do you really know this
weird old man here?
-Yes, I do.
Now you go and play
with this little child
that came with him.
-Oh, ho-ho.
He really stinks too!
-Hey!
Wait! you'll get used to it!
-So it's been quite a long time.
Sorry, but that's not
a cushion to sit on.
-Huh?
Oh.
I beg you pardon.
-There is much to talk about.
But first, sake.
SAORI: We walked so much
my legs are swollen.
KANA: I'll make you
a cold compress.
Shima, come on.
It's your turn.
SHIMA: I know.
I know.
-I'm writing you in search
for news about Yokai.
And now to send.
-Nurika be Ace.
-I doubt it!
-I thought Rikuo would be here.
Isn't he coming?
-I wonder what's keeping him?
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): The
shrines in our town
are being destroyed, and our
clansmen are being attacked.
Could they all be connected?
-Huh?
-Thank you for helping me
out of a dangerous situation
yesterday.
-Any time.
That's it!
Yesterday you were being
attacked by Kagibari Onna,
so I rushed over to help you.
At that same time, that
shrine was being destroyed.
I wonder.
-Master Rikuo?
-Thank you, Kejoro.
I know what the Shikoku
Yokai are after.
Gather everyone.
Listen up, everyone.
Split up and assign a
guard to every shrine
that has not been destroyed yet.
Do not leave your stations.
The enemy may try
something showy,
but that'll just be a diversion.
-A diversion?
-That's right.
They'll do something flashy
to get our attention,
while they carry out
their true purpose
for coming to Ukiyoe Town.
-And that would be?
-To attack the local deities.
They're trying to
cleverly undermine
the power of our clan.
Local deities garner the
beliefs and fears of humans,
and thus support the
foundation of the clan.
-If those deities
are eliminated,
the people will turn
to the Shikoku Yokai
to appease their
beliefs and fears.
-They'll weaken the framework
of the Nura Clan from beneath.
-Not only our clan.
They want control
of the whole town.
-We're not going to let
them have their way anymore.
I'm counting on you all.
Right.
-Master, everyone has
taken their positions.
-That's good.
Now all we do is wait.
-Huh?
-Do you really think it
was all right to leave
Nura's house like this?
-Shima.
-Yeah?
-It's master's school friends.
-Why are they here?
-Shima.
You saw the map, didn't you?
-What about it?
-When you connect
all the shrine ruins,
in the order in which
they were destroyed,
the arrows form of
tightening spiral.
So, in other words, the
next undamaged shrine
in the path of the arrows is
bound to be the next target.
And this is that shrine!
Mark my words.
Today is the day that I will
finally meet with a Yokai!
[shriek]
-So Kagibari Onna
went into Yokai Alley.
-Yes., but she ran
away pretty quickly.
-The enemy has begun
its diversions,
which means that a shrine
somewhere will soon be--
-Actually, master, we
may have a big problem.
Aotabo just called.
-Huh?
What happened?
Kiyotsugu and Shima
left the mansion
despite all the
warnings I gave them?
-I see.
Looks like I figured
it all out, Shima.
I received data
about that torn cloth
from a Yokai professor
who lives over in Shikoku.
-Shikoku?
-Yes.
Shikoku!
There's a Yokai that
comes from there
who is known for eating
kimonos and clothing.
This is him!
-Huh?
-Lord Sodemogi.
This Yokai specializes
in killing local deities.
You see, every town has local
deities, supernatural beings
that watch over
the land, and live
in these kinds of
hollowed shrines.
They're also known
as native deities.
-This one has a strange
and unusual appearance.
He must be the local
deity of this shrine.
-It says here that Lord Sodemogi
usually appears from behind,
then he reaches out
and pulls your sleeve.
If you turn and
look at his face,
you immediately become cursed!
If you don't wanna be
cursed, be docile, and let
him have the sleeve.
You're not supposed to resist.
-No way!
-What are those two doing?
-Hey, Shima, don't
pull at me like that.
I can't I type when you do that.
-Kiyotsugu, behind you.
-Behind me?
-No!
Don't look at it!
-Calm down, will you?
Don't bother me.
Shima, please!
SHIMA (VOICEOVER): Oh, oh.
What do I do?
If I don't do something fast.
Kiyotsugu will be cursed!
Of course.
I can use this.
The best of Japan's
under 14 soccer players.
-You're so annoying!
-This is my world
cup, so take that.
-You're bothering me.
-Kiyotsugu, are you all right?
-What's the big idea Shima?
-A Yokai, there was
a Yokai behind you.
-What?
-Those two destroyed the shrine.
-So this whole time
is was their doing?
-I doubt that.
Let's keep watch a bit longer.
-Wait.
Isn't that?
-I'm sure of it.
[giggling]
-Stop!
-Where?
Where did it go?
-I think it went
that way over there.
-Looks like they're
both all right.
Tsurara, get them out of here.
-Right.
Leave it to me.
-Damn it.
Is this the Yokai's doing too?
[giggling]
-So you're the one
who's responsible!
-You won't get away with it.
-What are you waiting for?
An engraved invitation?
Get out here and
help me already!
You can take over now.
-You won't pass, because
protecting Lord Sodemogi--
-Is our mission.
-Master, get away!
-Aotabo!
-Leave this overgrown oaf to me.
-You're the crows
from the other day.
-You're surrounded.
Give up.
-I, Inuhoo will
neither run, nor hide.
-C'mon.
Let's get him.
-I'll make you
regret those words.
-Stop acting brave.
[chuckling]
-My flames are invincible.
They will devour any
who dares to oppose me.
Turn to ashes and
scatter in the wind!
-You know who
you're dealing with?
I am Tearai-oni, the strongest
Yokai in all of Shikoku.
-Pretty impressive, but
you're not the only one
with brute strength around here.
Just in case you
don't know, the name's
Aotabo, the apostate monk
who wears an iron blue robe.
-Huh?
Uh-- mom?
MRS. NURA: What is it?
I'm busy.
[laughter]
-You expect to
beat me in the sky?
Not in a million years!
-Die!
-Look out!
[laughter]
-You won't even
make good yakitori!
-That bird's tougher
than I thought.
-This guy has
absolute confidence
in the power of his fire.
-He doesn't believe
for a minute that he
can be defeated by us in battle.
-Yes.
And that blatant arrogance
will be his downfall.
Let's go.
-And now for the final blow!
Die at the hands of Inuhoo, the
most skillful of the Shikoku
Yokai.
I Consider yourselves blessed!
What?!
How could I, the
great Inuhoo burn?
Done in by a bunch
of mere crows?
-You were burned by your
own ego and arrogance.
-Hoo the Firebird is
too good a name for you.
-After all, you're just a
dog, not even good yakitori.
-Time to go.
We'll settle out
little fight next time.
-They escaped.
[theme music]
KEJORO (VOICEOVER): Hey, Aotabo.
AOTABO (VOICEOVER):
Kejoro, you're
wearing a schoolgirl's uniform?
KEJORO (VOICEOVER): I borrowed
it so I can guard master.
how do I look?
AOTABO (VOICEOVER): Well
pretty good, in a way.
KEJORO (VOICEOVER): In a way?
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Next time--
"Natsumi and Lord Senba"