NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
Demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for
him, the Lord the Pandemonium,
Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
-What was that sound?
It was awfully loud.
Saburo Neko?
What happened to you?
-Huh?
Must be from that
last gust of wind.
Anyway, I'm fine.
My clothes just got
a little torn up.
-I see.
-I'm going to go change.
Supreme commander!
Master!
-Keep it down, will ya?
What's this all about?
-Something really
strange has happened over
at Bakeneko Alley.
-Oh, man.
There's always
something going on.
Hm?
I smell-- poison?
There's a nasty wind blowing.
GIRL (VOICEOVER): The Vanguard
Wind Blows From The West.
[laughter]
-Here you go.
Here.
-Another incident over
at Bakeneko Alley?
-Yes.
It's probably some
petty Yokai trying
to imitate the Kyuso clan.
There's no need for concern.
-I sincerely hope so.
-Say, supreme
commander, would you
consider letting me
handle this case?
-What?
-I'd like to get to the
bottom of this personally.
-No.
That won't be necessary.
Let the young ones
handle this case.
-Seeing Master Rikuo declare
that he would take over
as the third heir
yesterday brought back
memories of your younger days.
And it made me want to
stir things up a bit.
It's a little too soon to write
me off as a retired old geezer,
don't you think?
-Do as you please.
But don't come crying
if something goes wrong.
-I'll bring over some fresh
green tea leaves when I'm done.
We'll enjoy them together.
-Wait.
Don't forget the sweets
to go with the tea.
-I know.
-I'll bring your Kofuku Manju.
-Oh, Hihi.
You leaving already?
-Yes.
My, you look just like an
ordinary kid like that.
-Huh?
-Ryota Neko, tell
us what you know.
-They had come
here to investigate
yesterday's incident.
-It's hard to believe the
great Yokai Lord Hihi could
be killed so easily,
along with his men.
-But look at the clean
cut of this slash.
-A kill like this requires
extraordinary skill
and an extremely sharp blade.
-Or maybe--
-What is it?
-The wind.
There was a tremendous
gust of wind,
and when I went
outside to check,
I saw Saburo Neko's
clothes in tatters,
as though he had gone
through a shredder.
At first he seemed
fine, but then he
collapsed, and has yet
to regain consciousness!
-This is obviously
the work of outsiders.
-An enemy force,
totally unknown to us.
-Yes, and they have
boldly challenged
the supremacy of the Nura clan.
-We mustn't waste any time.
Let's go.
Take care of the rest.
-Right.
We must notify the main
family immediately.
-This is an emergency!
-Have Dad place the top
officials under heavy guard.
Hurry!
-Master.
-We just heard what
happened to Lord Hihi.
-Right after I make up my
mind to become the third heir,
something terrible like
this had to happen.
-Master.
-Why would anyone attack Hihi?
SASAMI: Master!
Master!
Master.
My father calls for you.
-Karasu Tengu does?
-Yes.
And also, he wants
you two, as well.
-Increase my bodyguards?
-What do you mean,
he needs more guards?
It's our duty to guard Master
Rikuo, and it always has been!
-Yeah, he's right.
Are you insinuating that
we're not strong enough?
-Don't the two of
you care at all
if something terrible
happens to Master Rikuo?
-Of course we do.
-We care!
But--
-I'm satisfied with
the way things are.
-No, master!
The fact is you are the
irreplaceable third heir
of the Nura clan.
If something happened to
you, it would be disastrous.
Until we learn
who attacked Hihi,
there will be six bodyguards
assigned to you at all times.
This is my final decision!
-Huh?
Kubinashi?
His head isn't moving.
Is that Kappa?
His webs are showing.
Kejoro?
-Oh, my.
It's so cramped in here.
-Why's she in a
school girl's uniform?
Wait.
Wasn't there one more bodyguard?
KUROTABO (VOICEOVER): Fools.
Don't they know how to
blend in with humans?
Take a good look at me.
I blend in perfectly.
I look like a
handsome businessman.
-Shoot!
I'm getting off!
[shouting]
-So who's the last one?
-It's supposed to
be Kurotabo, but--
-That guys probably off
playing hooky somewhere.
-Master!
-Stop it!
-But I have to follow you.
I'm your bodyguard.
-I said I don't need one!
I hate when people follow
me around like that.
[coughing]
-Lord Zen?
-What is this?
This runt is really
my bodyguard?
-I may be small, but
I have Yokai power.
-Watch it!
Hot!
Hot, hot, hot!
Cold!
-Oh, wow.
I wonder who we're
going to be guarding?
I hope it's somebody important.
-What are you, an idiot?
We're no more than
hostages around here.
Why are you excited?
-Everyone else is, and it's fun.
-Forget I asked.
-Ow!
Why'd you hit me?
-I only guard big
shots, or none at all.
-We're going to have to assign
someone extra strong to protect
you, supreme commander.
-There's no need
for such a fuss.
-You there!
Gozu, Mezu.
I'm putting you to
work right away.
-Yeah!
-You two are going
to be bodyguards.
-For that guy?
-That guy, you say?
How dare you refer to
him in that manner.
This Yokai here is-- who, me?
-He's gone!
Why, Sundokuchi?
Supreme commander?
Supreme commander,
where are you?
-This is stupid.
-That Karasu Tengu.
It's his fault Rikuo is
so damned overprotected.
-Look at that.
When did they put
this building up?
It's awfully big.
-Except it lacks beauty.
Those humans just don't get it.
[shriek]
-Ah, I take that back.
Tall buildings aren't
bad, after all.
-Supreme commander.
-It's almost complete.
We will make this
our sacred ground.
Now we can kill Nurarihyon, the
supreme commander of the Nura
clan.
-Rikuo.
-Huh?
-We're gonna be
late for our club.
Let's hurry.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I put you on the spot by asking
so many questions about him.
-Don't worry about it.
-You seem so distracted today.
-Huh?
-You just sat there quietly
in class the whole time today,
and you haven't even
cracked a smile.
Is something wrong, Rikuo?
-No, um, it's nothing.
I really didn't get much
sleep last night, that's all.
-I hope that's it.
You're always so
upbeat and positive,
I just get worried when
you're looking down like this.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): She's right.
If I'm down, I'll only
make everyone worry.
This is the time when I have
to be strong as the third heir.
-Uh, Rikuo?
-I really appreciate
you worrying so much
about me, Kana, but
I'm perfectly OK.
Really.
-Who Wants the
strawberry flavored one?
-I do!
-Me, me, me!
-Supreme commander.
Looks like you got lots and
lots of sweets again today.
-There's plenty for
you too, Natto Kozou.
I got some old lady
Uzami's disgusting candy,
bean jam buns, rice
crackers, and Kofuku Manju.
-I'll bring your
favorite Kofuku Manju.
-It's so hard to believe
that he is really gone.
That damned fool.
-Supreme Commander.
I wish I could find
some way to console you
about Lord Hihi's passing.
He's gone!
Supreme Commander.
You're not gonna get anything
even if you line up there.
-Really?
Why?
That girl over there
is the Onmyoji.
YURA (VOICEOVER):
This is a battle.
If I lose, I won't have
anything for dinner tonight.
-We'll begin our limited
time sale right now.
-Ah!
Which is a better deal?
I can't tell.
Oh, this is so hard!
There's no time
to think about it.
I lost.
-Thank you very much.
-Mad rush, wasn't it?
-Wait.
Aren't you Nura's grandfather?
-Mm.
I see.
So, you actually
came to Tokyo alone
to train and become
a great Onmyoji?
Admirable.
-No, not at all.
-However, the Keikain
are very famous Onmyoji.
Isn't it rather harsh of
them to make you do this?
-No.
It's OK.
They didn't make me.
I chose to do this.
I'm going to stay
motivated, and one day
defeat the great
Nurarihyon, the Yokai leader
who's said to
reside in this town.
-Ah.
You are very ambitious.
-This is such a weird situation.
-Well, that was the plan.
-Hm?
-But after I arrived
here, I lost my touch.
I totally misread the
presence of Yokai,
I got myself captured while
trying to protect people
from Yokai, and on top of that--
-Hm?
YURA (VOICEOVER):
I can't say it.
To admit being saved by a Yokai
is a disgrace for an Onmyoji.
-What's the matter?
-Oh, don't worry.
It's nothing, really.
YURA (VOICEOVER):
Why did that Yokai
come to our rescue like that?
-Can I ask you something?
Yokai are evil
creatures, aren't they?
-Why do you ask?
-Yokai are evil.
I was taught that and fought
against them until now.
But a lot of things have
happened since I came here.
And I've become-- I
don't know-- confused.
-There's really no need
to dwell over it, my dear.
Yokai are evil creatures.
I mean, they are what
they are, after all.
-Mr. Nura.
You're absolutely right.
Yokai are Yokai.
Their mere existence
is terrible.
I mean, what's there
to doubt, right?
-Yes.
There's nothing to doubt.
-Thank you so much, Mr. Nura.
I feel a lot better after
talking to you like this.
-Well, you're doing your best.
-Supreme Commander.
What are you doing
encouraging an Onmyoji?
-You know, if you're
ever troubled by Yokai,
please don't
hesitate to tell me.
I'll come and help
you, I promise.
-Thank you.
Keep an eye on Rikuo too, OK?
-Of course.
I have a feeling you and I are
going to become good friends.
-Well, I'm happy
to hear that, dear.
-What was that strange wind?
-It's probably an eddy
created by the closeness
of the buildings.
-Mr. Nura, look out!
-Shima and Yura are not coming?
-All right!
It's all done!
-Kiyotsugu, you made
something again?
-Yep.
Here.
Take a look for yourself.
-A map of Japan?
KIYOTSUGU: Not exactly.
This is a graph showing
the areas in Japan that
have had Yokai
sightings, and I've
included all data about
Yokai throughout the country.
-Looking at this graph, there
seems to be a lot in the west,
especially in Kyoto and Shikoku.
-That's right.
Shikoku has the largest
number of Yokai sightings
in the country.
I mean, you could easily
call it one big Yokai
kingdom if you wanted.
-I figured as much.
There are so many.
-Now for the best part.
Using all the data I
collected, I made this.
-Onmyoji what?
KIYOTSUGU: It's a game
featuring the Onmyoji girl that
covers all the Yokai data
in Japan as you play.
We can have fun and
learn about Yokai too.
It's killing two
birds with one stone!
-Wow.
You really do like Yokai,
don't you, Kiyotsugu?
-More like obsessed with it.
Can you show me what
Yuki Onna looks like?
-I wonder if the Yokai I'm
looking for is in here?
-Are you all right, Mr. Nura?
-Yeah.
-Oh, so you [inaudible].
You have some good reflexes.
-Who is that fellow?
-Kamaitachi, the Yokai
that manipulates wind?
-You know a lot about
Yokai, Mr. Nura.
-Oh yes, well--
-But that's not
Kamaitachi over there.
It's someone else.
I've seen him in one
of the books I studied.
This one is a wind
Yokai that makes
a sharp sound like a whip.
This whipping wind is
poisonous, and if you
sustain a deep wound,
it can kill you.
Its one of the Yokai found
in Shikoku, named Muchi.
Mr. Nura, run away!
-Karasu Tengu?
-Supreme Commander!
Where have you run off to?
I wonder if there's more
trouble in the clan again.
Wind formation,
striking sand whip!
-Look out, Mr. Nura!
-Hey.
Never mind about me.
-Can't do that!
YURA (VOICEOVER): I can't
protect him like this.
-Mr. Nura.
Hang onto this!
Rokuson!
-A Shikigami?
-Get him!
-Thank you for your
help, young girl.
-Supreme Commander!
-She may be a
Keikain clan Onmyoji,
but she is clearly outnumbered.
-Now you're going to
be the first to die.
-That's what she gets for
using a Shikigami to help me.
-No, Supreme Commander, don't!
You can't reveal your
true self to her!
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Good.
I'm finally free
of my heavy burden.
-Three Shinigami?
Unbelievable.
To summon this many at her age.
She has amazing skills.
-Tanro, Go and devour
every one of them!
Rentei!
A fourth one?
-Shikigami convert!
-Jinshiki Synthesis!
Keikain style, Onmyo jutsu!
Banish to the Abyss, Yura Max!
Did you think a young girl
like me was easy to defeat?
NARRATOR: Standing strong
in the face of evil.
Will the Onmyoji
girl's power put an end
to the wind Yokai
Muchi's bloodlust?
[theme music]
RIKUO: Say, Kubinashi,
are you a heartbreaker?
KUBINASHI: Huh?
RIKUO: Kejoro said
that's what you are.
KUBINASHI: Ah, did she?
Actually, I think that's
more like you, Master.
RIKUO: Huh?
NARRATOR: Next time, Tamazuki
and the Seven Shadows.