NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm, and led the night
parade of a hundred
demons was known
as the Supreme
Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium-- Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): The
power of the Nura clan
is known throughout the country.
The Gyuki Clan occupies Mt.
Nejireme located
at the Western end
of the Nura Clan's territory.
This is the story of how
its leader, Lord Gyuki,
came to rebel against the
Nura Clan's Third Heir, Master
Rikuo, an incident that has
brought lasting consequences
to the Nura Clan's future.
Lord Gyuki's Rebellion--
The Whole Story.
-You would be wise to
answer my questions, Rikuo,
and answer each one
of them clearly.
If I'm not satisfied
with any of your answers,
I'll cut off your ears and arms.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER):
Lord Gyuki was
born as a human being
over a thousand years
ago in what was then the
capital city of Japan.
-Mother, do not worry.
I will devote myself
to knowledge and train
in the way of the
sword, I promise
I will always protect
you in father's place.
[roaring]
[screaming]
-I curse all the gods.
I curse the Buddha.
I curse the world that stole
my mother and father from me,
and I swear that from this day
forward, I will become a demon,
and mourn my parents
by devouring humans.
-No!
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): When Lord
Gyuki lost his mother that day,
he renounced the name his father
had given to him, Ume Wakamaru,
and became Gyuki, a malicious
Yokai that devoured humans,
and spewed hate.
[growl]
-Haa!
You must be Gyuki
-There's no need to tell you my
name when you're about to die!
[shout]
-I must say, you're very strong.
The rumors were right about
your strength and talent.
Why don't you consider
joining my clan.
How about it?
-Hey.
Karasu Tengu.
-Yes
-Go look into our
clan roster and see
if anyone was in
contact with Chozo.
-You think there's
a traitor among us?
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): Lord
Gyuki carried out his plan
very carefully.
One day Master Rikuo and the
Kiyijuji Paranormal Patrol
went to visit a place
called Ume Rakuen.
However.
Ume Rakuen turned out to
be none other than Mt.
Nejireme.
-What are you talking about?
-It's a small shrine, and
I think a Jizo statue.
-What is all this?
-Those, Miss, are claws.
-Claws?
-The Yokai live right up
here on this mountain.
You can't let a mere
torn off claw scare you.
And the best part is that the
hero of this mountain's Yokai
legend, Ume Wakamaru,
is up there.
-I simply can't believe that
he would actually do that.
Hm.
-Rikuo isn't coming home today?
-No.
He's gone on an
outing with his club.
-Karasu Tengu, why don't
you join me for some tea?
-Yes.
I'd really like that.
-So where did Rikuo
and his friends go?
-He said they were all
going to Ume Rakuen.
-He went to Ume Rakuen, eh?
Well, I think that's
a great place.
-Oh.
So you've been there before?
-But supreme commander,
that mountain is--
-The fray has come
to the mountain.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER):
Until finally-- Oh, look.
It's me in there.
-I mean this is a
truly historical spot.
-Watch out, master!
Oh.
It's just a raccoon dog.
-All right.
This is the Yokai spot
known as the One-Eyed Pine.
-Hm?
-Let's pass through
one at a time.
-I'll go first.
-Wait a minute.
I wanna go through it first.
I wanna make sure it's
safe and sound before I
let anyone else try it.
-OK.
Let's move on, shall we?
-Yes.
Now you get to
see how cool I am.
-It's frozen.
-Who are you?
Do you belong to the Gyuki Clan?
-So what if I do?
-I warn you.
Don't do anything stupid.
Now, do you have
any idea who I am?
-I see.
You're a Yuki Onna.
-If you know, then
put away your sword,
and you will not be
blamed for any of this.
[chuckling]
-What's funny?
-You know, if I were you,
I'd cut the laughing.
You don't seem to realize
who you're messing with.
Who do you think
my master is, huh?
-Why don't you just
shut your damn mouth!?
Don't underestimate our clan.
We're putting our lives
on the line for this.
-You mean Lord Gyuki sent
you to kill Master Rikuo?
-The ever discrete Lord
Gyuki planned everything!
Die!
RIKUO: Tsurara!
-No, master!
Run away!
-Tsurara!
-You're too late!
-Master.
-You call that a fight?
I feel sorry for the blade.
A coward like you can't
even dodge my claw!
Gozu Shadow Claw!
-Master, watch out!
Master!
-Yuki Onna!
Damn it.
-The meaning of the Gyuki
Clan's emblem of terror
is to manipulate, bewilder,
lure, and kill humans.
There's no way I'd lose
to a mere human like you!
-Ha.
To a mere human, huh?
-This is the end
for you, Rikuo Nura!
How could I lose to you when
you're not even a Yokai?
-The blood flows through me.
The evil blood of the
Supreme Commander.
That's how.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): I
still have some bruises
from that fight,
but enough about me.
What's really important is
that Master Rikuo and Lord
Gyuki were meeting
face to face, alone.
-Where is Zen going?
-He seems like he's in
an awfully big rush.
-Supreme Commander.
-Lord Zen.
-Is what I heard true?
Has Rikuo-- I mean has
Master RIkuo gone up to Mt.
Nejireme?
-It seems that news
reaches you rather quickly.
-I know this is
none of my business,
but I must have my
say, Supreme Commander.
Recently, I've gotten
a strange feeling
from Gyuki and some of the
many Yokai that serve him.
Is it wise to ignore this?
-I will leave his
all up to Rikuo.
-But, sir.
-Any objections?
-Tell me what's on
your mind, Gyuki.
-So you've come after all.
I see.
It seems you really do have
the supreme commander's
blood in you.
When morning comes
again to the mountain,
will you go back to your
weak and fragile human form,
and forget everything
while you were a Yokai?
If the day does not
recognize your Yokai form,
are you one person by
day, and another by night?
-Perhaps.
Why is it you're so
concerned about me?
-Fool.
-My resolve has
remained the same
since my blood
awakened that day.
I will become the Third Heir
and rule over all Yokai.
-Haa!
-Well done, Master Rikuo.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): The
duel between two great Yokai
ended with Master
Rikuo's victory.
-Rikuo.
-I'm here.
GYUKI: Listen carefully.
Mt.
Nejireme is the western
border of the Nura Clan.
The clan has no influence with
other Yokai beyond that point.
From here I can
see it all clearly.
Unless we act now, our
clan will fall apart
from within and without.
That is the reason
for all my actions.
I won't tolerate anyone who
dares to try and destroy
my beloved Nura Clan, even
if that person is you.
But I was wrong.
You were able to defeat me.
You have proven to have
the skills and the will.
And now I shall finish
what I have started!
Why did you stop me, Rikuo?
Why?
I must take
responsibility for this
as the one who plotted treason.
Why didn't you just let me die?
Now I'll never be able
to face Gozu and Mezu.
-Gyuki, you've made your
reasons quite painfully clear.
Once you confirmed
I was weak, you
would kill me and then yourself.
But I turned out
to be legitimate,
and yet you still chose death.
That is very much like
you, but you know what?
There's no need to die.
This is nothing.
All right.
Let me be your father
from now on, Ume Wakamaru.
-Honestly I wanna live
in peace, but there
are people I need
to protect, and I
know I'm going to have to
rely on this blood to do that.
So, you see, if there's
someone like you around who I
can trust, someone who
loves this clan so much,
I want them to stay, and
be a part of the family.
-Family.
-Yeah.
Anyway, you just get some rest.
Thus, with regard
to this incident,
I judge Gyuki not guilty.
There is no sentence, and
I take full responsibility
for what happened.
That is why the Gyuki Clan will
remain a part of our family.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): Lord
Gyuki finally accepted
Master Rikuo as the Third Heir,
and pledged to support him
and the Nura Clan.
And that's the whole story
behind Lord Gyuki's Rebellion,
an incident that changed
the Nura Clan forever.
[theme music]
TSURARA (VOICEOVER):
Shima, Why do
you hang around with Kiyotsugu?
SHIMA: Because he's super rich.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): Oh.
SHIMA: No.
Wait.
I mean he's super cool.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): Uh-huh.
-Next time-- the
Inugamigyobu-Tanuki, Tamazuki's
Beckoning.