NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
demons was known as the
Supreme Commander of the Yokai
They had another name for him.
The Lord of Pandemonium.
Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
[birds calling]
Nurarihyon.
Are you familiar with
the tamazusa plant?
-You mean the snake gourd?
Tamazusa is what we
call a letter today.
The shape of the
snake gourd seed
bears a striking resemblance
to a knotted letter.
And so, tamazusa was given as
an alternate name to that plant.
-Wow.
Looks like your useless
trivia knowledge
came in handy this time.
-Be quiet, Natto.
-A millennium ago, the
retired Emperor Sutoku
raised a large army to try and
unseat the reigning Emperor
Go-Shirakawa.
His tragic defeat led to his
exile, here to Sanuki province.
For the rest of his
life, Sutoku became
teary-eyed when he heard the
chirping of the nightingale,
which brought back memories of
the ancient capital he left.
Legend has it, the nightingale
was so saddened by this,
it wrapped the leaf of the
tamazusa around its beak
in order to force
itself to be silent.
-He knows quite a
bit of trivia, too.
-It is because of
that legend I decided
to name my son Tamazusa.
I wanted him to grow
up to be understanding.
To know right from wrong.
But instead, my son
decided to change his name
to Tamazuki, which means
"to covet the throne."
And now he seeks to rule
over all Yokai in the land.
[rain falling]
[thunderous crashing]
[grunting]
-Oh!
[growl]
[gasp]
-Someone is approaching
from the west!
-How many?
-One!
[grunting]
-It looks like he's hurt.
-He's one of us.
Let him come through.
Do not attack him.
-I bring a message.
-That can wait.
You need to get treated.
-Master.
He was desperate to deliver
whenever news he has for you,
despite his grave injuries.
You must hear him
out, right away.
-All right, then.
Tell me.
-Right before sunrise this
morning, Shikoku Yokai
crossed Chichibo Pass
with a large army.
-The Chichibo Pass?
-See to this Yokai's injuries!
-Move out of the way.
-Well, it's just as well,
because I'm itching to flight.
-The fortress at
Chichibo was supposed
to be cleared out because
of the imminent danger.
So why would a messenger
come from there?
-In order to relay news
until the very last moment,
some chose to risk
their lives and stay.
-Just for us?
-That was a very foolish
thing for them to do.
-I'm going to go help Kujoru.
-I'm coming with you.
-You know, if we'd just
been able to stop them
at Mount Nejireme, the situation
may not have come to this.
-Those guys knew that
the Nura clan was still
recovering from
the internal feud
and used it to their advantage.
-This really pisses me off.
-Me too.
-Shikoku was once home
to countless Yokai.
And for Tanuki
Yokai especially it
was considered a
virtual paradise.
-Ugh.
I wonder If I should
speak up and tell him
that his tail is still showing.
-There was a time when Tanuki
Yokai outnumbered humans
in your territory.
Isn't that right?
-Yes, that's true.
But 300 years ago, an
ill-omened incident
occurred that changed
all that forever.
-Oh.
-We, the Tanuki Yokai,
attempted to usurp a castle
from the humans.
-A human castle?
-Our foes were
mere human beings.
In contrast, we were
a large Tanuki Yokai
army with supernatural powers.
For us, nothing
seemed more certain
than a decisive victory.
However, instead of victory,
our army of Yokai was massacred.
-They were massacred?
You mean every one
of them was killed?
-That's right.
We were defeated by a single
blade wielded by the humans.
-Hmm.
You mean the Devil's Blade?
The legacy of the conqueror.
-We've received word that our
reinforcements have passed
through the entrance to
Kanto, Chichibo Pass.
They are expected to arrive at
Ukiyoe Town before midnight.
-Goo.
Is there something
else, Kagibari?
-You haven't asked a
thing about Inugami.
-All right.
What is he doing now?
-He's just sitting
there, not moving at all.
It's as though he's
waiting for his moment
to come with every
fiber of his being.
-Huh.
Are you scared, Kagibari?
-No.
Of course not.
What's there to fear when
we have you to lead us?
[panting]
-So this is a
sleeper train, huh?
I always wondered what it
was like to ride in one.
-Huh?
-Since it's a private room, I
thought I'd get comfortable.
You know about
kodoku, don't you?
-Yes.
Of course I know about it.
-The "ko" in the
word "kodoku" is
there to signify the presence
of many poisonous insects mixed
together on a single plate.
To survive, the
poisonous insects
kill each other off
until only one remains.
That last insect is infused
with the hatred and curse
of those who were killed.
And thus, the cursed creature
known as kodoku is created.
-Huh?
Woah, jeez!
-The Devil's Blade
your son possesses
can strengthen itself with
the blood, flesh, and hatred
of all of those who
are killed by it.
Just like koduku.
-Precisely.
I've not seen a more
terrifying weapon.
-The blade that massacred
the army of Tanuki Yokai
in one swoop.
The Devil's Blade!
-Natto Kozo, pass me a
can of beer, will you?
-Huh?
-You heard me.
Now hurry up.
[panting]
ANNOUNCER: The landslide at
Chichibo Pass this morning
is still under investigation.
-You're Kana Ienaga, aren't you?
[gasp]
-Don't worry.
I don't have a long
tongue like Inugami.
And I won't try to
lick you like he did.
[whimpering]
-Don't you want to
know about that Yokai?
-What Yokai?
-Well, who do you think?
KANA (VOICEOVER): He has the
same feel as that other person.
TAMAZUKI (VOICEOVER): Hmm.
He's trying to protect
someone like her?
What a strange guy.
What does he see in this human?
-Please tell me.
-What?
-You know.
About him.
-Hmm.
Well, he and I are much alike.
You see that, don't you?
He and I have a lot in common.
We've both been entrusted with
the responsibility and power
to rules over Yokai.
-You're wrong.
He isn't anything like you are.
-Really?
That's interesting.
What's different about us?
Just what do you know about him?
Do tell.
I'm very curious.
Are you afraid of me?
-No, of course not.
Why should I be?
-Oh?
-I don't like you, that's all.
-Hmm.
-You and he are very different.
I mean, I don't know why,
but I can say this much.
I'm sure that inside
he's a good person.
-Huh.
-Oh.
-Um.
That's what I think.
-If you say so.
[gasping]
-Get the hell away from her.
You're a Yokai, aren't you?
-Well, well, well.
If it isn't the Onmyoji girl.
-Ienaga.
Are you all right?
-Yeah.
-Perfect timing.
Now, you listen to me, Yokai.
I don't care what you
Yokai do among yourselves.
Go ahead and kill each
other all you want.
It'll make my job
that much easier.
However, I will not allow
you to harm any humans
while you fight your little war.
You remember that.
-It's been worthwhile seeing
just what it is that the enemy
Commander cherishes so much.
And quite nauseating.
I assure you, the next time
we meet, I'll show no mercy.
[gasp]
-Now, then.
What was your name again?
-Yura Keikain.
Onmyoji.
Remember it well.
-Until we meet
again, Miss Keikain.
-Oh!
OK
[theme music]
[background chatter]
-I shouldn't just be lying here.
-Did you hear?
-Yeah.
We're finally going to war.
-But the Supreme
Commander isn't back yet.
-Can we rely on
Master Rikuo alone?
-Of all times for
him to be away.
-I hear the enemy's destroyed
our fortress at Chichibo Pass.
[shouting]
-The Shikoku Yokai could
attack us at any moment now.
What is keeping the
Supreme Commander?
How could he be missing
at a time like this?
-Never during the
past few hundred years
did I ever imagine that the Nura
clan would come under attack.
-I'm scared.
-There's no point
in complaining.
In fact, I say it's time we
stand behind the third heir,
and take the fight to our enemy.
-Not so fast, Zen.
You're putting the
cart before the horse.
We need to know how
Master Rikuo feels first.
-Hmm.
-Fine.
I agree.
Let's go ask Rikuo, I
mean, the third heir,
what he thinks we
should do right now.
-Someone!
-You summoned?
-Where is the third heir?
-Well, I think he's--
[sigh]
-What's the matter?
-In the foyer.
-The foyer?
-Huh?
[concerned chatter]
[sigh]
-Master.
-Hey, there.
How about it?
Want to join me
for a little drink?
[humming]
-Yes.
Thank you, Master.
-I would be honored to join you.
-Me first, Master.
-I don't believe it.
Is that really Rikuo?
-Our young Master is
becoming quite the leader.
Don't you agree, Hitotsume?
-Ha.
He's hopeless if
he thinks he can
save the clan with
a bluff like that.
-Hmm.
-I'm coming in, Lord Shoei.
-Did something happen?
The mood suddenly seems to
have changed quite a bit
around the mansion.
-Yes.
And it's all thanks
to Master Rikuo.
-Huh?
-I'm certain now that Master
Rikuo will do something.
-Ha.
-The time has come.
Our curse will
finally be broken.
[panting]
-Inugami.
I inherited my father's
supernatural powers
when I was born.
But I quickly learned that
such powers were useless,
especially to a clan who'd lost
their edge 300 years earlier.
There wasn't a single thing
for me to do in the clan.
Such intense eyes aren't needed
in today's Shikoku, Tamazuki.
That was the value
placed upon me.
I will never forgive all
of those who shunned me.
Today I understood a little
of the jealousy that you feel.
Inugami.
I will surpass my father today.
Crushing the Nura clan is
only just the beginning.
[growling]
-What's he doing?
-The Devil's Blade is
crying out for more.
What it wants is more blood.
More hatred to feed upon.
-Oh!
-Behold, my brave
Shikoku Yokai warriors!
Our glorious moment of
victory is now at hand!
Have no fear of the Nura clan!
Kill to your heart's content!
-Yeah!
-The Shikoku Yokai
are on the move now.
-They're marching towards
the main street in Ukiyoe.
-That's far enough.
-Lord Hitotsume.
-Please, wait, young Master.
-What is the meaning
of this, Hitotsume?
You don't intend to block
Master's way, do you?
-Please make way for
us, Lord Hitotsume.
-Yeah!
-Be silent.
I'm talking to Master
Rikuo right now.
-Master.
What is all this?
What do you think
you're doing here?
Taking on the Shikoku Yokai
in the untimely absence
of the Supreme Commander, and
without the express consent
of the clan's
executive committee,
is an exercise of sheer folly.
-You're right, Hitotsume.
-Huh?
-So, then.
You're in agreement with me.
-Come on.
Not you, too, Gyuki.
We can't sit back and do nothing
at a critical time like this.
-It is because we were at
such a critical juncture
that we must proceed
with the utmost care.
Now, if Master Rikuo
were to mobilize
only his own Night
Parade of 100 demons--
-Huh?
-Hey.
Wait a minute.
-Heading out to battle
becomes an option.
We cannot stop
Master Rikuo then.
-Grr.
Fine.
You have a point.
If the third heir takes only
those pledged to him then
he can do whatever he wants
at his own discretion.
Of course, it remains
to be seen how
many will actually joining him.
And even if everyone
here in the mansion
opts to go on this
foolish mission,
the numbers will still
fall rather short.
Do you still think we have a
chance to defeat their army?
-Huh?
-We can't win?
-Third heir.
I would like to
hear your answer.
Do you really think we
actually have a chance
to win this fight?
-The Nura clan can never lose.
-Quiet, Aotabo!
We should never take the 88
demons of Shikoku lightly.
And you should
know that, Aotabo.
[birds cawing]
-Oh.
-A large mass of Yokai
aura is coming towards us
from the southeast.
-It is?
-There's more coming from
the northwest as well.
Wait, from the northeast, too.
-Oh, no!
The enemy is attacking already?
-Oh!
-It seems they made it in time.
-Huh?
-Master.
In response to the
circular you sent out,
many clans have sent proxies
who have hastened to join us.
-Thank you.
Excellent work.
-This Yokai aura.
The sheer quantity
is extraordinary.
-Oh, yeah.
Now we're talking.
-Master never
ceases to amaze me.
-I'm in love all over again.
-Gozumaru.
Are we just going to sit
around here and do nothing?
-Pff.
Weren't you listening to
what Lord Gyuki just said?
-Huh?
-Let's go.
-Right.
-Come on, everyone.
Let's go!
-Yeah!
-Oh, you foolhardy sons of mine.
I've never been more proud
to be your father than today.
[crying]
-Cripes.
Old men are such sentimental
softies, aren't they?
-Oh.
[theme music]
-Lenaga.
You really treasure your
hand mirror, don't you?
-Mirror, mirror, in my hand.
Who is the prettiest human
or Yokai in the land?
-You, Kana.
-OK.
That was weird.
-Next time.