-In days of old,
people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
Demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
[horn]
-I might not make it
in time to stop you.
Huh, Tamazuki?
-Hm?
GIRL (VOICEOVER):
The Devil's Blade.
-I sense the presence of Yokai.
A whole lot of them.
KANA: Wait!
Yura!
-You don't need to come, Ienaga.
It's dangerous.
[groan]
-There.
That should do it.
SHOEI: Take care of these guys!
You need to tend to
them quickly, OK?
-Shoei.
What about you?
Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
Hurry up and see to them.
-I just can't believe that
even Gozumaru and Mezumaru have
been wounded badly like this.
-Stop running and
fight me, Kappa!
-What, so I can make this
little game easier for you?
Forget it!
-Aotabo, you and I are gonna
settle our little score today,
once and for all.
Well, it seems like I am
the stronger one here.
Wouldn't you agree?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
-He took out the Nura
clan's strike team leader!
-I guess I just proved
that I'm the strongest
Yokai in all of Japan!
-Prepare to die!
-There's nowhere left
for you to run now!
-I wasn't running away.
I was looking for more water
to create a bigger attack.
Like this!
Kappa Ninja Special,
Mizuchi Ball!
Yeah!
[scream]
-No one bailed
you out this time.
Heh, heh.
That was pretty fun.
[laughter]
-This is like taking
candy from a baby.
[squish]
-Huh?
My-- my arms.
No-- my shoulders!
-I had completely
forgotten my own strength.
You see, I have to keep my
powers in check at all times
to avoid causing problems
in the human world,
because I'm too strong.
I'll show you just how
strong I really am.
[groan]
-I guess it's true.
The weaker you are, the more
you want to be part of a pack.
I, Kurotabo, the Assassin Monk,
show no mercy to my enemies.
Who else wishes to taste my
Dance of the Black Weapons?
-Give up already?
You guys don't stand a
chance against the Nura clan.
Not in numbers, or
in sheer strength.
Not to mention beauty.
-Grr.
Untangle me!
-It's useless.
These strings are made
out of Kejoro's obsession
to not let go of her loved ones,
combined with a joro spider's
relentlessly possessive nature.
-If you're going to give
up, now is the time.
-Not a chance.
I'm not giving up!
The Shikoku Yokai is
destined to be victorious,
and will rule over all Yokai.
-Why do you want to
keep fighting so badly?
I mean, is your commander
really all that charismatic?
-What?
Yes, of course he is.
Lord Tamazuki's
powerful command of fear
brings everyone to their
knees and inspires them.
-Command of fear, huh?
-Tamazuki is going to create
a glorious new Yokai world!
-Well, it looks like the battle
is beginning to go against us.
-But that doesn't
seem to bother you.
-Because I expected
this would happen.
-What?
-They're all weakness,
each and every one of them.
I never thought for
a moment that we'd
have a chance against you.
-Tend to my wounds later.
-Don't be a fool.
You'll die.
-We need to let Rikuo
know right away.
-However, even a hopeless lot
can be quite useful sometimes.
-Master Rikuo!
-Stay back, Yuki Onna.
-Yes, that's right.
I'm going to use you all.
-This-- this Yokai aura--
-It's Tamazuki.
-Huh?
-Tamazuki!
-Dammit!
-Lord Tamazuki?
-Why is your leader
slaughtering everyone
in his own Night Parade?
-That sword of his-- it's alive.
-Master!
It's dangerous.
Please, step back now.
-Lord Tamazuki!
They're your own people!
Please stop!
Weren't you going to take us
all to a brand new Yokai--
-Lord Tamazuki--
HARI (VOICEOVER): That's right.
I always knew-- but I just
didn't want to admit it.
I wasn't drawn to
Tamazuki's fear.
I was just plain
scared, so I obeyed him.
Inugami-- what about you?
-Tamazuki!
You call yourself a leader--
-Kubinashi!
-Don't, Kejoro!
Get back!
-Hey, let go of me!
I won't be satisfied until
I slap his stupid face!
[laughter]
-Rikuo!
-Wait.
The devil's blade?
-That's right.
It's Tamazuki's sword.
-The sacred sword
of Shikoku legends.
It's said that with it, you
can destroy Yokai and conquer
the world.
It gains power by absorbing
the strength of every Yokai
it kills.
-I see.
Hm.
-Lord Tamazuki!
-Please, stop this!
-We beg of you!
[shouting]
-Come on, hurry up, everyone.
The Yokai are waiting
for us, so let's go!
-I don't exactly wan them to
wait, if you know what I mean.
-I don't get why
we have to go, too.
-Oh, man.
I can't believe how
fast Kiyotsugu is.
-Hold on.
What's this hideous Yokai aura?
-I'm getting a weird feeling.
-Yeah.
Me, too.
-You two better get back.
-Huh?
-There you are, Yokai!
Go!
Tanro!
[roar] Rokuson!
-What's that girl doing there?
-Uh, was that a deer?
No way.
It couldn't be, could it?
YURA: Bukyoku!
Rentei!
Stop!
You're not going any further!
Vanish into the abyss!
Yura Max!
Huh?
-It's Yura.
And wait, is that-- a Yokai?
-What is this guy?
YURA (VOICEOVER): His
Yokai aura is massive,
but I have to exterminate him.
I must.
I can do it.
Have faith!
Remember, I am the heir to
the Keikain clan of Onmyoji.
-An Onmyoji?
Ah, yes.
You're a Keikain, wasn't it?
-Your rampage ends
right here, evil Yokai!
I will not allow you to spread
distruction and hurt people.
Yura Ma--
[shout]
-Heh, heh.
-Get back, or you'll be killed.
-It's you, the
lord of all Yokai.
-I'll take care of this guy.
You go and protect the humans.
-I don't take
orders from a Yokai.
Wait a minute.
Did you just say protect humans?
But you're an evil Yokai.
-He swept in and protected Yura.
MAN: My shameful son Tamazuki
is trying to surpass me.
BOY: Huh?
What do you mean by that?
MAN: Remember the
300-year-old story
I told you earlier,
about the huge Yokai
army that was
annihilated by humans?
The commander of the vanquished
army sits here before you.
-Huh?
-Tamazuki is ashamed
of me because I
was defeated by humans,
and still continue
to lose my strength.
That's why he's
doing all this now.
-I obtained the devil's
blade that defeated my father
centuries ago, and through
its ability to multiply power,
I became strong.
And Yokai followed me.
This is what fear means.
This is fear!
I came to realize
that, and now my fear
has finally surpassed
that of the Nura clan's
supreme commander!
-It's all over, Tamazuki.
-Stop!
Let me go!
-Bastard!
-The tables have turned now.
-Let the girl go, Inugami.
[laughter]
-Humans always seem
to distract you
right at the most
critical moments.
It's all because of
your ridiculous ideas
about protecting them.
-Protect humans?
Really?
-Humans and Yokai
can never coexist!
Never!
-You lose!
What's the matter?
Make your move, if you dare!
Now's your chance, Tamazuki!
Go on, kill him!
-Not a very elegant way
of doing this, is it?
INUZAMI: Do it, Tamazuki!
Hurry!
Chop this sorry excuse
into little pieces!
Tamazuki will open
up a whole new world
where Yokai will be superior,
and rule over humans!
The dawn of the
Shikoku Yokai is here!
-No!
RIKUO: Don't worry.
-You shouldn't act
so brave, you know?
-Kana, if you're
scared, close your eyes.
If you're scared,
just close your eyes.
[tires squealing]
[crash]
[car horn]
BOY: It hurts!
-I crave some fongoli.
Yeah, that's right-- fongoli.
-You're still alive.
Ha ha ha!
I'll kill everyone.
Sending all of you children
to the depths of hell
is what I enjoy doing.
-Master!
We made it in time.
-Gagoze, a Yokai that
kills little children.
I'm glad everyone is OK.
-Who are you?
Tell me.
-Huh?
-If you're scared,
just close your eyes.
Taking pleasure from
killing the weak,
harming people and
stepping on corpses.
Well, now you must answer to me.
-You're just a kid.
Don't get so damn cocky!
[groan]
-Let it be known
to every Yokai, I
shall be the Lord
of Pandemonium.
Follow me and be part of my
Night Parade of 100 Demons.
-Huh?
[groan]
KANA: That's right.
I remember now.
Even back then, he protected us.
I'm OK.
I trust you completely now.
So I'm not scared at all.
-Quit your nonsense!
If you can still act that
brave after he's dead and gone,
then I might just
consider praising you.
I'm going to kill
him and complete
Tamazuki's collection of fear.
Our time has finally come!
Now take me to the
new Yokai world!
I swear I will follow
you until the very end!
INAZAMI (VOICEOVER): I'm
going to follow Tamazuki.
He was the one who awakened
my sleeping powers.
And he promised me that he would
take me to a brand new world.
I want to see that world.
I'm very glad that I met him.
-Inugami, there's no one in
this world more loyal than you.
-Heh.
[coughing]
-Tamazuki, what's the matter?
Why are you doing this to me?
Tamazuki?
Why?
TAMAZUKI: I'm grateful to you.
[groan]
-With your strength, the devil's
blade will attain perfection.
You were a truly
loyal dog to me.
However, I don't
like dirty methods.
-But-- but I-- I
did it all for you.
TAMAZUKI: I feel it.
This power.
This is fear!
-Tamazuki, this fear you
keep harping about-- tell me,
are we supposed to feel
it emanating from you?
No one's going to
follow a guy who
bears the corpses
of his comrades.
The supreme commander of
Yokai isn't like that.
TSURARA: He's strong.
KEJORO: Intelligent.
AOTABO: And you
just can't hate him.
MAN: That's why we all--
MAN: Follow him.
-I took a liking to the
supreme command, Nurarihyon.
I may be physically stronger,
but I'm no match for him.
He is a true Yokai, and yet he
understands the human heart.
-I get it now, Dad.
Fear is--
-Admiration.
[laughter]
-You and I are alike.
At least, that's
what I believed.
-No.
You are nothing like him.
-She's right.
-It seems I was wrong.
We are destined to
be on opposite sides,
so let us end this
fight right now.
And I will build my own
new world for Yokai!
Now, awaken, devil's blade!
[theme music]
GIRL: The Shikoku Yokai,
Inugamigyobu Tanuki Tamazuki
versus the Nura clan's young
heir, Master Rikuo Nura.
Their fight finally
comes to an end.
NARRATOR: Next time,
The Moon Is In The Sky.