NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm and led the night
parade of a hundred
demons was known
as the Supreme
Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for
him-- The Lord of Pandemonium--
Nurarihyon.
[thunder]
-Master.
-Tell me what's on
your mind, Yuki.
-So.
You've come after all.
Then it's true.
There's no doubt that the
blood of the Supreme Commander
flows through you.
And yet, when the
new morning comes,
you will return to being
a human once again.
And then, will you completely
forget that you are a Yokai?
If the day does not
recognize your Yokai form,
are you one person by
day and another by night?
-Perhaps.
Why is it you're so
concerned about me?
YUKI: Fool.
[thunder]
-My resolve has
remained the same.
Since my blood
awakened that day--
[grunts]
I will become the third heir,
and rule over all Yokai.
-(SLEEPILY) Huh?
NARRATOR: The handsome knight
Rikuo is only 12 years old.
The question is, will he be
the one to lead all Yokai
and inspire true fear?
[thunder]
-All Yokai will
follow me and become
my night parade of 100 demons.
[thunder]
NARRATOR: "Becoming the
Lord of Pandemonium"
[birds chirping]
RIKUO: All right.
Is everyone here?
-Yes.
Every member of the Nura
clan is in attendance.
-Thank you, Master.
It's great that you've
summoned us here.
-We couldn't be more
honored as your retainers.
-It is fitting that
you, as the third,
have called us all together.
Yes, yes, indeed.
-Come on.
You're being dramatic.
C
-OK, Master Rikuo.
Who are we up against?
Give us the order and
we'll go kick their butt.
-It's nothing like that.
I called you together to
make a request to all of you.
-Request?
-You have a request for us?
-Yes.
Now listen.
You're all forbidden from going
near the old junior high school
building tonight, understand?
-You mean the building that
stands right behind the school?
-Mm-hm.
You all know the one I mean?
-But how come we can't go there?
-Because I said so.
Anyway, just stay away from
there and do not go near it.
I'm off to school now.
-Uh, you're up early, Rikuo.
I haven't packed your lunch yet.
-It's OK.
I'll buy something at school.
-Please!
Wait a moment, Master.
It's dangerous for you
to walk outside alone.
You should at least
take a sword with you.
-I'll be fine.
I'm just going to school.
[gasps]
Yuki!
-Well, well.
If it isn't Master.
-It's been a while.
How are you?
-I'm glad to see that you
are looking very well today,
Master Rikuo.
Nothing could please me more.
-Well, got to go to school now.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Boy.
Yuki always looks so scary.
-Lord Yuki.
-It's a pleasure
to see you, sir.
-I know this might sound
rather far-fetched,
but Lord Yuki wouldn't try
to usurp Master's position
as the third, would he?
-He could try, but I'd
never allow such a thing.
[sound of water running]
YUKI: Greetings,
Supreme Commander.
-So you've come, Yuki.
-His appearance has
always been human,
but Master Rikuo even
thinks like he's one.
In any age, we Yokai should be
held in awe by humans, dreaded,
in fact, as ones who are
capable of instilling true fear.
We live in strange
and difficult times.
Perhaps we should now
reaffirm the solemn oath
we made on your emblem.
-Master!
You must succeed the
Nura clan, or else.
-Enough.
Will you stop following
me around, please?
-Oh!
-Humph.
Why should I care about Yokai?
I just want to be an
average human and--
-Kana!
Did you hear about the
old school building?
-The old school building?
What's that?
-It's right here on
the school grounds,
but no one is allowed
to go inside of it.
I hear that it's
haunted by Yokai.
-That's so scary!
-Yeah.
-Oh, come on.
There's no such thing as
Yokai, is there, Rikuo?
-Uh, r-- right.
GIRL'S VOICE: I'm starving.
BOY'S VOICE: Time to eat.
-By the way, guys, are you all
going to make it for tonight?
-You bet I am, Kiyotsugu!
You're going too, right?
-Mm-hm.
-All right.
What are you talking about?
-Tonight, we are going
to explore the old school
building.
We're going to look for Yokai!
GIRL'S VOICE: Huh?
Really?
-You're really into
this Yokai stuff.
I don't get it.
It's just an empty building.
You probably started the
rumors about it yourself.
-They're not rumors.
I saw them with my own
eyes, four years ago.
Yokai really do exist.
GIRL'S VOICE:
You're lying, right?
Come on, there's no
such thing, right?
KIYOTSUGU: I know
what's going on here.
You guys are just
afraid of Yokai.
-Not really.
We don't know
anything about Yokai,
so how could we
be afraid of them?
Right, Rikuo?
-Mm-hm.
KIYOTSUGU: In that case, why
don't you come and join us?
It's your big chance
to learn about Yokai.
-Uh, but it's too
dangerous for girls.
-It's OK.
I don't mind going there.
And besides, there's
no such thing as Yokai.
[gasps]
GIRL'S VOICE: Oh!
-Well then, tonight you will
see with your own two eyes
that Yokai really do exist.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
It's a good thing
that I told my guys not to go
anywhere near the old school
building tonight.
[crickets chirping]
CHILDREN: Come on, play.
Play.
Come on.
Play with us.
Don't you want to play?
Come on.
Play.
Let's play.
Come on.
-I can't.
Sorry, but I'm a
little busy tonight.
CHILDREN: Play.
Please.
Play.
Play with us.
-OK.
CHILDREN: Aww.
(LAUGHING)
-I'm up!
CHILDREN: Want to play.
It's boring.
Boring.
It's so boring.
-Hey!
CHILDREN: It's so boring.
-Come on, you guys.
Get to work.
Finish sweeping the
gardens by dawn.
CHILDREN: OK.
-OK, grandpa.
I'm going out with
my friends now.
-Just a minute, Rikuo.
-What is it, grandpa?
I'm sort of in a big hurry.
-Be honest.
Have you given any thought to
succeeding me as the third?
-Oh, not that again.
I'm not going to change my mind,
no matter how many times you
ask.
-But a quarter of my blood
runs through your veins.
You can't deny that, no
matter how much you want to.
-Well, I intend to live
my life as a normal human.
I made up my mind long ago.
See you.
WAKANA: Oh, are you going out?
Be careful, now.
-Thanks, mom.
-Bring me some sake.
-Oh, all right.
[traffic noises]
-Oh, this is so creepy.
-Um, tell me right
away if you get scared.
-Mm-hm.
I'll be fine.
There's no such thing
as Yokai, anyway.
-Course not.
[laughing]
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Why am
I getting this bad feeling?
No.
We should be fine.
I made myself clear to them.
GIRL'S VOICE: Are we, uh,
really going inside, Kiyotsugu?
KIYOTSUGU (LAUGHING):
This place really
looks haunted, doesn't it?
[laughs]
KIYOTSUGU (LAUGHING):
I'm sure of it.
There's got to be Yokai in here.
-Oh, no.
It seems I'm feeling a
little scared after all.
-Uh, don't worry, Kana.
We won't see any Yokai tonight.
-Why is that?
-Oh, that, um, well, it's
because if anything happens
here tonight, I'll protect you.
-Really?
You will?
[boy screaming]
[girl screaming]
[scared noises]
-These are just a bunch of
old paintings and sculptures.
-Huh?
Let's look around the
room and check it out.
-Oh, OK.
-Nura, go check the
shelves on that side.
-Mm-hm.
-Hey.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Damn.
A Yokai was just
hanging out here,
and she's not a
part of Nura clan.
-Hey, is there
something wrong, Rikuo?
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): More of them?
What clan are they from?
-I think it's a small pantry.
-Uh, you want to check it out?
-Uh, sure.
-No!
Wait!
-What in heck was
that for, Nura?
-Uh, sorry.
-Uh, did you see
something, Rikuo?
-Um, no.
I just got thirsty
all of a sudden.
[moaning]
-I want to drink blood.
I crave blood so badly.
-But I guess I can wait.
[laughing]
RIKUO: Follow me.
I'll lead the rest of the way.
Oh!
There's nothing
here in this room.
It's all clear here, too.
[growling]
Oh!
[flushing]
-Huh?
-Ah.
I feel much better now.
[growling]
-Eek!
-Nura!
-What's going on?
-Oh, it's nothing.
Really.
Don't worry about it.
Oh!
This is getting ridiculous.
BOY'S VOICE: Well,
there's nothing, is there?
-I don't understand it.
According to my
investigation, this place
should be haunted
from top to bottom.
-Guess there's no such
thing as Yokai after all.
-You see?
That's what I've been
saying all along.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
There's so many Yokai here
I've never seen before.
Everyone here is in danger.
KIYOTSUGU: Oh well.
Let's just take one last
look in here before we go.
[door creaking]
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): This place.
Oh!
It's bad.
Really bad.
[growling]
-Oh!
-Kana!
Kana!
-Oh!
[growling]
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): I
have to protect Kana.
But how?
[growling]
[glass breaking]
-Oh!
-Aotabo always gets
so carried away.
-Yuki Onna!
-Rest assured, Master Rikuo.
I've come here to protect you.
[growling]
-Don't you lay a
hand on our master.
We are your opponents.
YUKI: Supreme Commander.
Do you know how
many years it's been
since the second
heir passed away?
You were already retired.
How long will you continue
to stand in for him?
-I have told you all
time and time again.
The third heir to lead the Nura
clan and its 72 organizations
comprised of 10,000 Yokai
will be my grandson, Rikuo.
-Yes, but Master Rikuo
is still so very young.
-And I have heard that
Master Rikuo has no desire
to succeed you.
-Unbelievable.
-Supreme Commander, is what
they speak of the truth?
-I have also heard that
he awakened his Yokai
self only once.
And that was four years ago.
YUKI: Everyone
makes a valid point.
[murmuring]
However, the character
fear is written
as a demon holding a whip.
Namely, it represents the
ruler of the world of darkness.
Let us wait for the
day when Master Rikuo
takes hold of the whip
and inspires true fear.
[murmuring]
[growling]
-Freeze to your death.
[howling]
[grunting]
[laughing]
RIKUO: All right, you two.
Why did you come here?
-Master, we've been
guarding and protecting you
since that fateful
day four years ago.
-And we're always by your side.
-Always?
-We'll explain it later.
Our first priority is
to get you out of here.
[crickets chirping]
-Oh.
Oh.
-You see, we both watch over
you wherever you go, ever
since that night
when you awakened
to your other
self, Master Rikuo.
Does this appearance
look familiar to you?
-Huh?
Oikawa and Kurata
from class one?
-Yes.
Master, it is very important
that you succeed your father
as the third heir.
-We will wait however
long it takes.
-Oh.
-We'll wait for the
glorious day when
you will rise up and lead the
night parade of 100 demons,
just as you did four years ago.
I told you.
I don't remember a single
thing about that day.
I'm just a human being.
-Master.
-And I want to stay
that way, as human.
[traffic noise]
-Uh?
-Kana!
-Where are the Yokai?
The monsters?
-Wait!
It's all right, Kana.
There weren't any Yokai there.
-Do you mean it?
-Mm-hm.
Really.
-Oh.
Thank goodness.
[traffic noise]
-I'm home.
-Good evening.
Welcome back, master.
-Oh, wow.
-Come on, Kana.
We have to finish our homework.
[poof]
-If I had jumped in just
a few seconds later,
we might have seen
our Master awaken.
-Uh-huh.
RIKUO: Never mind that.
Come on, let's go.
WOMAN'S VOICE: Have some tea.
GIRL'S VOICE: Uh,
pleased to meet you.
WOMAN'S VOICE: My,
what a very cute guest.
I'd be so happy if someone like
you married into this family.
RIKUO: Mom!
WOMAN'S VOICE: Oops.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, make yourself at home.
RIKUO: Geez.
Oh--
NARRATOR: Rikuo Nura briefly
transformed into a Yokai.
Will the day come when he
wields the demon's whip
and inspires true fear?
[theme music]
-When did your head
become so long, grandpa?
-I started to lose my hair and
then my head became this way.
Heh.
One day, you'll be like me, too.
-I don't want to.
-Next time, Poison Wings
Flutter in the Bamboo Thicket.