[music playing]
NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm and led the Night
Parade of a Hundred
Demons was known
as the Supreme
Commander of the yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
[thunder]
YUKI ONNA: "Cold-Blooded
Umewakamaru."
NIGHT RIKUO: Tell me
what's on your mind, Gyuki.
-So you've come after all.
I see.
It seems you really do have
the Supreme Commander's
blood in you.
To appear wherever
you like so elusively.
-Elusively, huh?
Now answer me, Gyuki.
Why?
Why would you be so foolish
as to try and kill me?
You're known for making very
careful but wise decisions.
So why?
Were you the one pulling the
strings behind the Kyosu Clan?
-When morning comes
again to the mountain,
will you go back to your
weak and fragile human form
and forget everything
while you were a yokai?
If the day does not
recognize your yokai form,
are you one person by
day and another by night?
-Perhaps.
Why is it you're so
concerned about me?
-Fool.
-My resolve has
remained the same
since my blood
awakened that day.
I will become the third heir
and rule over all yokai.
If I felt like it, I could
easily cut off your head.
-You would be wise to
answer my questions, Rikuo.
And answer each one
of them clearly.
If I'm not satisfied
with any of your answers,
I'll cut off your ears and arms.
You see, you're not
the only one here
who is capable of cutting
off heads if he chooses.
-Illusions, huh?
-Did you transform on a whim?
Remember that time
when you killed me too.
-Were you aware that the Nura
Clan has weakened considerably
since the death of
the second heir?
-Do you have any
intention of taking over?
Answer me now.
-This world has lost
all sense of order.
Are you willing to do what
it takes to restore it?
-I want to know.
-Rikuo, answer me.
-Gyuki, what are you planning
to do after you kill me?
-I will kill you, and
then I will die as well.
I have heard that there was a
time when the capital, rather
this entire country, was struck
by frequent natural disasters
and war, and thus was
severely impoverished.
-Look.
Rain has started to fall.
-The rain is a blessing.
-Yes.
-The Hiyoshi Gongen shrine is
known for bringing miracles.
I'm sure it'll
grant us our wish.
GYUKI: Yoshidano Shosho Korefusa
was a high ranking noble,
and he had a wife named Hanako.
Hanako had been unable
to conceive a child,
so they set out for
the Hiyoshi Gongen
shrine in the province of
Omi to pray for a blessing.
However, to their dismay,
she remained barren.
Then--
-It was such a strange dream.
But just then, I was
surrounded by a wonderful scent
of freshly picked plums.
-A scent of plums?
I think that this
must bode well for us.
-I agree.
I was thinking that too.
GYUKI: The following spring
when the plum blossoms were
in full bloom, a
baby boy was born.
They named him--
-I have decided on Umewakamaru.
-Umewaka, let us get going.
GYUKI: When Umewakamaru
was seven years old,
his father Yoshidano
Shosho Korefusa
was known as a
just man but became
embroiled in political strife.
Officially, his
death was said to be
caused by a grave illness.
-Mother, are you crying?
Mother?
-What is wrong, Umewaka?
Are you not able to sleep?
-Mother, do not worry.
I will devote myself
to knowledge and train
in the way of the
sword, and I promise
I will always protect
you in father's place.
Mother, you are hurting me.
I can barely breathe.
GYUKI: Umewakamaru
was sent off to pray
for his father's repose.
But the truth was
that his mother
was remarrying in
order to survive.
Thus, Umewakamaru entered
the monastery at Mount Hiei.
-Father, Mother.
GYUKI: Time passed,
and as it did,
Umewakamaru matured
into a fine prodigy,
acknowledged by everyone
as a talented youth.
News of his mother's
illness was devastating
to the 12-year-old Umewakamaru.
His desire to see his
mother was so strong
that he was willing to abandon
his studies and his future.
-Pardon me.
Pardon me.
Young man.
Sorry to wake you, but is
your name is Umewakamaru?
GYUKI: The two claimed to have
served Hanako since shortly
after Umewakamaru was sent away.
And--
-Your mother is recuperating
at the residence that
is up the road not
too far from here.
-In spite of her
terrible illness,
she has been longing
to see you again.
-Mother is nearby?
-Yes, sir.
She is staying in a mansion
about half way up a mountain
called Mount Nejireme.
-Mount Nejireme.
Let us go there now.
-I know that your mother
will be so surprised.
-She will.
-Ladies, how much
longer until we arrive?
GYUKI: It was all a cruel lie
to deceive an innocent youth.
[ground quaking]
[roar]
-I was tricked.
-That won't be any use to you.
-Umewakamaru's first
thought was I want to live.
I have to live until I can
see my mother one more time.
[growling]
But the demon read his mind.
-Your mother, how
very interesting.
Could this be who
you're looking for?
You know, noble folk
are so very, very tasty.
GYUKI: The sword that held so
many memories of his father
was useless, and he could
only stand there helpless
as his beloved mother
was devoured by a yokai.
-Lord Gyuki, are you all right?
-I curse all the gods.
I curse the Buddha.
I curse the world that stole
my mother and father from me.
And I swear that from this day
forward, I will become a demon
and mourn my parents
by devouring humans.
-Oh please, please spare us.
We did not want to do it.
We were forced by Gyuki
to lure travelers to him.
He said he would
kill us if we didn't.
-We are so grateful you
have exterminated Gyuki.
Thank you, my lord.
-No need for
gratitude because you
will offer your
own precious lives
in memory of my murdered mother.
[screams]
GYUKI: Mourning his
mother, Umewakamaru
attacked humans again and again.
He recruited yokai from
the area to join him
and continued his bloody rampage
until he became known as Gyuki.
Several decades,
several centuries
passed, by then,
Umewakamaru, rather Gyuki,
had long forgotten about
the love from his parents.
That is when he
finally appeared.
-So is that Gyuki's
mansion up ahead?
-Yes.
-Supreme Commander.
-You must be Gyuki.
-There's no need to tell you my
name when you're about to die.
-Interesting.
No one is to interfere.
This one's my prey.
Huh?
GYUKI: The battle raged on for
three days and three nights.
And I was trounced, defeated
utterly, humiliated.
As the leader of the vanquished,
I was prepared to be executed.
-I must say.
You're very strong.
The rumors were right about
your strength and talent.
Why don't you consider
joining my clan?
How about it?
Perhaps, you can't make
up your mind just yet.
I'll give you two days.
Come see me before
the two days are up.
GYUKI: Two days passed.
[carousing voices]
[hushed whispers]
-I won't allow you to come
any closer to the Supreme
Commander.
-Don't worry.
It's all right.
-But Supreme Commander.
-Supreme Commander?
-You've come at last.
I've been waiting for you.
-I swear my loyalty.
The entire time
he was testing me.
He threw himself
at me and beat me.
And then, acknowledged me.
I completely lost to him.
For as long as I live,
I'll never forget the words
Lord Nurarihyon said
to me that night.
Never.
[theme music]
RIKUO: Hey, Night
Rikuo, how old are you?
NIGHT RIKUO: Yokai aren't
concerned with age?
RIKUO: But someday, we'll
also become old like Grandpa.
NIGHT RIKUO: Don't
ever say that.
RIKUO: So you do care.
NIGHT RIKUO: Next time,
"Gyuki's Beloved Nura Clan."