(VOICEOVER) In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
demons was known as the
Supreme Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for him.
The Lord of Pandemonium.
Nurarihyon.
[theme music - in japanese]
-This one's destroyed, too.
-This is the second one today.
You think a Yokai is
behind all of this?
-That's what we're going to find
out with this investigation.
We can't let Yura and the
girls beat us to the answer.
-Oh, right!
-This was their plan all along.
To destroy the local
deities and weaken
the Nura clan's source of power.
They carefully executed
it so that we wouldn't
realize what's really happening.
The 88 Demons of Shikoku and
Inugami Gyoubu-danuki Tamazuki.
-Hey, it's kind of
dark and scary here.
-Yeah, especially since we're
right behind the hospital.
-Hey.
I think we found one.
-Oh.
-It's filthy.
It's so old it's hard to tell
if it's been wrecked by someone
or not.
-The deity of this
shrine must be ancient.
Maybe people stopped
coming and the shrine just
collapsed because
it was neglected.
-I never knew this shrine
existed in our territory.
-Hey there, everyone!
-Huh?
-What do you say
we call it a day?
We should go back to the
house before it gets too dark.
-How come?
Do you have some
sort of curfew, Nura?
-No, it's just that my mom
will have dinner ready soon.
-Hey, I've got a great idea.
Yura, why don't you
come over to the house
too and have dinner with us?
-Huh?
-It's not your house, you know.
-You really should join us.
Wakana's cooking
is totally awesome.
-Yeah, her doughnuts
were fantastic.
Maybe I will join you after all.
-Huh?
-Hey, what's the matter, Rikuo?
-Oh, uh, it's nothing at all.
-You're not worried
that your mom's
going to break more
dishes, are you?
-Let's go back, then.
Everyone stay alert
for any signs of Yokai.
We'll keep investigating
until we get home.
-Our plan seems to be
moving along smoothly.
-But Tamazuki, those
Nura-clan weaklings
are onto our strategy.
Last night, they
didn't take the bait
during the ruckus
at Yokai Alley.
Not only that, they managed
to take down Inu Hou-ou.
-Calm down, Tearai Oni.
-There is no need to panic.
-Huh?
-Fool.
You turned around
and looked at him.
-Give him your sleeve
before it's too late.
-Huh?
Oh!
-Take it easy.
Last night we had
interference, but today I
promise to exterminate all the
local deities of this town.
-That's some
confidence you have.
With that spirit, you won't
be needing to have any guards.
[panting]
-All right.
Gather around, everyone.
It's time for our daily
Kiyotsugu Yokai storytelling
session.
-OK.
-Sorry, count me out.
I'm going to go help Mrs. Nura.
-Hey, come back!
-Boy.
Another tiring day.
I'd better touch up my makeup.
Huh?
What are you doing, Natsume?
-Oh, it's nothing.
-Oh.
Origami!
-Hey, come on.
What are you doing over there?
And where's Oikawa?
Has anyone seen her?
-Oh, yeah.
Where did she go?
-Here you are.
I've been looking for you.
-Yeah.
Don't worry.
I'll go back in soon.
-Are you thinking about
last night's Yokai?
-Grandpa told me the local
deities-- they're frail.
But they provided support
to the Nura clan for ages.
-Master.
-That's why we have
to put a stop to this.
Kuromaru.
-As you ordered.
We've tightened the
security around every shrine
in this area where local
deities are known to live.
-Good.
Thank you.
You know, we put guards
at just about every site,
but it just doesn't
seem to be enough.
-We're using crows
from all over town
to keep an eye on
every location we can.
But our territory is enormous
and includes dozens and dozens
of smaller local deities
that we aren't even aware of.
-Master.
-Speaking of smaller shines
we never knew about--
-Huh?
[giggle]
-That Ao is unbelievable.
He was supposed to
trade shifts with me,
only to show up 20 minutes late.
He's always like that.
It drives me crazy.
-Huh?
-Oh!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
-Damn!
It's Master's classmate!
-Uh--
[giggle]
[sigh]
-Huh?
-Hmm.
That is probably the
shrine of Lord Senba.
-Lord Senba?
-I've never heard
that name before.
Can you tell us what
kind of deity he is?
-He is an ancient
local deity who
was said to possess
healing powers.
He used to gather a lot
of the people's faith.
-I see.
[gasp]
-Hey!
Nura, Oikawa., where have
you two been all this time?
-Yeah, Oikawa?
-Oh, we just uh-- huh?
Where did Kana and Tori go?
-Kana is helping
your mom with dinner.
Nastume is-- I have no
idea where she ran off to.
-What?
-Until a while ago,
Tori was folding origami
and not paying any attention at
all to the story I was telling.
-Yeah, paper cranes!
Oh my best day, I can only
fold a simple sailboat.
[running footsteps]
-Not again.
-Man.
What is their problem?
-Hmm.
-I'm sorry I haven't
been coming by lately.
Lord Senba?
I want to thank you for
that time you helped us.
Hmm.
There.
[gasp]
-Oh-- I'd better hurry back.
-Stop!
-Oh!
-Praying to a rusty old deity
like this won't work, you know.
You should call my name instead.
I am Lord Sodemogi.
[whimpering]
-Call out my name now!
[screaming]
[wild laughter]
-Ah!
Who the hell are you?
A Yokai from the Nura clan?
-What did you do to this girl?
-Kurotabou!
[gasp]
-What happened?
[theme music]
-What exactly happened, Nura?
-She's going to be OK, right?
-Huh?
-Tori won't die, will she?
-She'll be OK.
I won't let that happen.
But, Rikuo--
-Really?
You really meant
it, right, Nura?
-Hmm.
Stay here, everyone.
You too, Oikawa.
-Huh?
-Kuro!
-Master!
Please forgive me.
I was near, and yet
I allowed our enemy
to endanger the
life of your friend.
I swear to you,
right here and now,
that I will find that
Jizo Yokai and force
him to tell us a way
to save the girl.
-Unfortunately--
-Huh?
-Who is there?
-That may not be possible.
I am Senba, the ancient local
deity who is enshrined here.
Master Rikuo.
I am honored to meet you.
-Lord Senba.
You're him?
-Yes.
I've lived in these
parts for a long time,
healing the illnesses of all
those who came here to pray.
-Well, then, can't you
use your healing powers
to save Master Rikuo's friend?
-No.
What ails that girl is a curse.
At this time, I am
not powerful enough
to break such a strong curse.
I'm sorry, but I
cannot heal her.
-Are you saying there's
nothing we can do to save her?
Not even with the
power of a local deity?
-In that case,
we'll have to break
the curse by defeating Sodemogi.
-Yes.
-Then we have no time to waste.
-Good thing the moon is rising.
Oh.
Hmm.
-You summoned us, Master Rikuo?
-I want you to go
and find Sodemogi.
He and I have a big
score to settle.
-Right.
-Just leave the fighting to us.
Come on, Kuro.
-Yes, sir.
[birds cawing]
-What's going on?
-Crows out at this
time of night?
[laughter]
[cawing]
-Master!
Master Rikuo.
I found him in the woods.
-Sorry, but it seems Ryota Neko
beat you to it, Tosakamaru.
Kuro.
-Right.
-Hey.
What's with the
long faces, guys?
-Huh?
-There's no use in
fretting like that.
The only thing we can do is stay
positive and try and support
Tori the best we can.
-You're absolutely right.
-Sometimes you say
just the right things.
But still--
-Here.
-I get it.
-What a great idea!
-Yeah!
[giggle]
-Sode, Sode, Sode.
Mogi, Mogi, Mogi.
Sode, Sode, Sode.
Hmm.
This will be the
last one for today.
[laughter]
[gasp]
-Who are you?
-That's a pretty
delicious-looking kimono.
-What do you want?
Do you realize who
you are dealing with?
I am Princess Koke,
the local deity
of this time-honored Tamakoke
shrine, which you are defiling.
Now get away!
[laughter]
-It doesn't matter who you are.
Because I am about to
curse you to death.
[laughter]
[scream]
-What?
What is this?
-Unfortunately, that sleeve
you crave belongs to me.
But if you want it so
badly, I'll give it to you.
[gasp]
-Ahhhh!
[screaming]
-If you have any
sense of taste at all,
that must have tasted awful.
For as you can see, my
sword tastes only of blood.
-Ahhhh!
-The last sleeve that you
will ever grasp in this life
will be the one from
your own death robe.
[wheezing]
-Are you done?
Answer my question.
Once you die, your
curse will be broken.
Is that right?
-Oh, you mean that
human girl, don't you?
[laughter]
-Yeah, the curse will
be broken, but that girl
will still die nonetheless.
My curse eats away
at one's life.
It's too late to save her.
[machines beeping]
[whimpering]
-If only I had the power.
[sirens wailing]
-Lord Senba, I came
here to give you
my thanks for curing my
grandma of her illness.
-When deities are forgotten,
and no one comes to pray,
they fade away.
-Hmm?
-It is especially true of
local deities like myself,
whose existence is maintained
through people's faith.
No one comes to
pray to me anymore.
Does that mean I will fade away?
As that thought crossed through
my mind, you came to me again.
It is because of you
that I am still here.
-Now, let's hang these
1,000 origami cranes
to pray for Tori's recovery.
-What are her vitals?
-It's gone below 100, Doctor.
Diastolic pressure is under 60.
-Oxygen.
Stat.
-Her saturation
level is decreasing.
Start an IV.
Under 85 now.
-Hurry with level one.
-She's on oxygen now.
-Watch for SPO2.
TORI (VOICEOVER)
What's happening?
Am I going to die?
[gasp]
-Natsume.
Natsume.
-Who's there?
Lord Senba?
-I am a weak deity.
But as long as someone believes
in me, I will not disappear.
The depth of people's wishes
makes my power stronger.
-It seems we made it
just in the nick of time.
-Yeah.
In time for me, too.
-I heard Lord
Sodemogi got killed.
-Don't worry.
It's according to plan.
But it's disturbing
how well the clan
is faring without their
Supreme Commander leading them.
Rikuo Nura, huh?
-You are the only one fit to
take control of this world.
Shall I prove it to them?
Give me the order, and I'll
gladly bring you his head.
-No, there's no need
to kill him right now.
He's merely a piece
of decoration.
-It is necessary.
We must show that damn Nura
clan the vast difference
between Rikuo Nura
and you, Tamazuki.
Come on, Tamazuki.
Let me be your fangs so
I can tear him apart.
-Hmm.
[panting]
-Mmm.
-Is it OK for you to
be running like that?
-Yeah.
I feel just fine.
-But it's like there was
nothing ever wrong with you.
It's so strange.
-I believe that this
is also connected
to the rash of
Yokai incidents that
have been happening
all over town.
-There's a good
chance that you're
right about that, Kiyotsugu.
-You guys always think
there's Yokai involved.
-Yeah.
But thanks, everyone,
for being there for me.
-However, I think
the one who really
saved her was the
deity of this shrine.
-Hmm.
(VOICEOVER) A gentle
breeze fills the air,
carrying with it
the scent of summer.
[theme music - in japanese]
-Say, Maki.
We've seen quite a
few Yokai, haven't we?
-You are so right.
-So how come Kyotsugu
hasn't seen any yet?
-I don't know.
Maybe the Yokai just
can't stand him.
-Next time.