[music playing]
NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm and led the Night
Parade of a Hundred
Demons was know
as the Supreme
Commander of the yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
YURA: "The Rat of
Darkness Devours the Cat."
[roar]
-Damn that girl.
She's pretty strong.
NARRATOR: The onmyigo
girl is on a mission.
Her skills will
vanquish the ayakashi.
-That's a good boy, Tanro.
-Hey, Kyuso, who is this girl?
-Yeah.
-Kyuso, giant rat
yokai that devour cats.
I never expected one to
disguise itself as a person.
-I never expected him
to befriend an onmyogi.
The third heir has an
interesting taste in girls,
doesn't he?
Why don't you put away
that dangerous toy?
-Don't touch me, you rat.
-Well, you may be
a skilled onmyogi,
but you're still just
a young little child.
[scream]
-No, stay away.
Help me.
-Stop it now.
She has nothing to do with this.
-Seems you were so
distracted by my good looks
that you forgot all about
your little friend over there.
Ah, but there's really no
need to be embarrassed.
You just couldn't help yourself.
-No.
-Now then, why don't you put
that shikigama of yours away?
KANA: Yura!
YUKI ONNA: Everyone,
dinner's ready.
Come and get it.
-Thank you for the
help, Yuki Onna.
-This is nothing, Lady Wakana.
You know I'm always happy
to help you out with stuff.
-What's wrong, Kubinashi?
-That sewer rat earlier,
he's from the Kyuso Clan.
-Indeed.
And speaking of the
Kyuso Clan, they've
seized control of First
Street from the Bakeneko Clan
and are causing trouble there.
Kubinashi, have you heard
from Ryota Neko, head
of the Bakeneko Clan?
-Hey, were you talking
about Ryota Neko?
-Yeah.
You see he's one of Kubinashi's
oldest friends, so I thought--
-The Bakeneko Clan have always
been gamblers, but not the best
fighters.
I'm not surprised they
lost to the Kyuso Clan.
-Neither am I.
[chattering]
-Hey, better hurry up
and serve the food.
-Sorry for the wait.
-What's with this?
-Boss, go.
I'll handle these rats.
Get out of here.
-Let's go.
Boss, keep running.
Don't stop.
-I'm sorry.
-What?
Not another rat.
-Are you Master Rikuo?
-Oh good.
It looks like you're
friendlier than the last one.
-How do you do, Master Rikuo?
I am a rat who runs errands
on behalf of Kyuso Clan.
-The Kyuso Clan?
-Yes, we are a group
of petty yokai rats
who live on Ukiyoe
Town's First Street.
-So what business does a
rat like you have with me?
-I've come to inform you of
something that's happened.
I witnessed two of your friends,
Yura Keikain and Kana Ienaga,
being abducted by a group
of dangerous criminals.
-What?
Abducted?
You sure about this?
-Yes.
I'm positive.
They were kidnapped
off the street.
-No.
This is terrible.
Thank you for coming
here and telling me.
-No, Master Rikuo.
Miss Keikain is an onmyigo.
You can't ask everyone in your
clan to help you save her.
-That's true.
But still--
-It'll be all right.
If something happens, my clan
will be there to help you.
Please, you need
to go by yourself.
-OK.
Let's go.
-Where's he going?
The master will get mad if
he finds out I followed him.
That place definitely
smells like bad news.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Kana,
Miss Keikain, hold on.
I'll save you.
-How do you do, Master Rikuo?
I'm Kyuso, and I'm the head
of the Kyuso Clan of yokai.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Welcome to our place.
-You tricked me.
-Sorry.
I told my men to give
you a proper welcome,
but they misunderstood.
No matter how useless
and cowardly you may be,
you're still, after all, the
third heir of the Nura Clan.
-Let the girls go.
-The emblem of the
Nura Clan no longer
has the power to satisfy
the desires of our clan.
No one cares about honor
or about loyalties anymore.
Those are all
things of the past.
Do you understand?
RIKUO: Kana!
Miss Keikain.
-I do this for the
sake of your clan.
Your clan won't be able to
survive with the old school
yokai you lead.
I want you to announce that you
will not become the third heir.
-OK.
You'll let the girls
go if I do, right?
-By tonight, I want you
to notify all clan leaders
in the country of your decision.
And if you fail at completing
what I've just asked of you,
I will kill both of these
girls at the very first light
of dawn.
-You OK?
Looks like you're hurt.
-Master Rikuo, I'm so sorry.
My name is Ryota Neko, the
head of the Bakeneko clan.
I was left in charge of First
Street by your grandfather.
-Listen.
You're hurt.
Just try and take it easy, OK.
-Master Rikuo, I
know the things we do
must look terrible to
you, but we do have rules.
We've been very careful not to
take the name of the Nura Clan.
-Hey, someone come
out here and help.
-But they're different.
-Master!
-Ryota Neko.
-What a waste.
I mean you're not really going
to return these kittens to him,
are you?
-Don't ask me stupid questions.
These beauties are
too good to let go.
Don't worry.
We're all going to have
plenty of fun with these two.
-[whimpering] This is bad.
-Ah.
Onmyogi girl,
finally awake, I see.
-Ienaga.
I told you she has
nothing to do with this.
Just let her go.
-You still don't
understand, do you?
I'm going to teach you that
without your shikigami,
you're just an ordinary girl.
No one's going to
come to your rescue.
KARASU: Master Rikuo, what
is the meaning of this?
-It's exactly what you see.
Karasu Tengo, I want you
to send these letters out
to every clan leader across
the country right now.
If you don't, Kana and Miss
Keikain will be killed.
KARASU: No.
I can't.
Don't do this, master.
You must reconsider.
An official letter
like this is as
absolute as a letter
of excommunication.
-I know that.
But in order to save them, this
is something I've got to do.
Grandpa.
There's nothing you
can do to stop me,
because I've got to save them.
NURARIHYON: The Kyuso Clan, huh?
-Wait.
You knew?
You knew about them, and
yet you ignored this.
Grandpa!
-Well, let's see now.
If I'm not mistaken,
they were some trash,
I removed from the clan.
RIKUO: Dammit.
I hate yokai.
You're all the same.
[whimper]
-Rikuo, it's your
responsibility to settle
what happened between
you and the Kyuso Clan.
You do know that, right?
-Yes.
I know.
-You won't regret this.
-I don't have any kind of power.
This is all I can do.
I have no choice.
RYOTA: Master, you mustn't.
-You shouldn't be moving.
-Besides, the Kyuso Clan never
keeps their promises to anyone.
-Ryota Neko.
-Supreme Commander,
I'm sorry, but it
was my cowardice that caused
this whole mess to begin with.
I swear to you now that will
bring an end to what I started.
-Ryota Neko.
Stop.
What can you do
in your condition?
-Master, there are
times in life when
a yokai must stand and
fight even though he
knows he will lose the battle.
RIKUO: Ryota Neko.
-Kubinashi.
-This will be our first
fight together in ages.
Show a little spirit.
[heartbeat]
-My blood is--
[hearbeat]
--boiling.
NIGHT RIKUO: NIGHT
RIKUO: You already know.
-I don't know.
I have no power.
I'm a human.
NIGHT RIKUO: No.
You should know about the
true power within you.
Don't worry.
I'll carry out your fight.
-Aw.
-Wait, you're--
-We're going to go hunt rats
until the break of dawn.
KYUSO: Did you know
that human blood
is at its most thick and
delicious just before dawn?
-You stay away from us.
If only I had a shikigami.
-Wishing you had this
little scrap of paper?
YURA (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
Please someone save us.
-Hey, Kyuso, what is that?
-I've only heard tales of it.
I think that it's the Night
Parade of a Hundred Demons.
-What are you doing?
Who ordered all of
you to mobilize?
Only the lord can
mobilize the night parade.
-The lord is right before you.
-What?
-This is the grandson of our
Supreme Commander Nurarihyon.
He is to become the
next lord of the yokai.
-So did you send out the
letter like you promised?
-Are you referring to this?
-What are you doing?
-Bastard.
-Get back.
-Quickly.
-So that's the
Supreme Commander?
-Yura, we've got to hurry.
-Right.
-Seems the cats have escaped.
-Dammit.
You won't get away with this.
I'm going to kill you all.
-Hey, Kuro.
Let's see which one of us
can take down the most.
-Die.
-Dance of the Black Weapons.
-That's cheating.
-That is the best compliment
you could give me.
I am Kurotabo, the assassin
monk of the Nura Clan.
Huh?
-While you're there
trying to look cool.
I'm scoring points.
-Oh my.
Well, if it isn't the
head of the Bakeneko Clan.
I believe your name
was Ryota Neko.
Are you injured?
-I'm your opponent.
-Master Rikuo, you're
letting him fight.
-Please let me do this, master.
I've got to avenge my henchmen.
I must honor the sacrifices
they all made for my clan.
-Oh, how very old
fashioned of you.
-Ryota Neko, wait!
-This is for my henchmen.
-Ryota Neko, are you all right?
-Of course, I am.
-Is that all you've got.
I'd like to play with you more.
You're mildly amusing for a cat.
But there's just no end to you.
-What?
-I'll deal with you two
after I kill your leader.
What is this?
-Meikyou-Shisui "Sakura."
It burns everything
until the ripples quell
and the liquid stills.
If you hadn't come after me,
you may have had a chance.
I wasn't planning
on getting involved.
-The Nura Clan is tied by its
obsolete rules and traditions.
Your clan has no future.
I want it gone.
I want freedom.
-The next time we meet,
I promise to defeat you.
-Until then.
NARRATOR: The
morning mist dampens,
leaving the young girls
to their thoughts.
What path will they
take from here?
Only time will tell.
KANA (VOICEOVER): Why do
I feel like I know him?
NIGHT RIKUO: It's
misty this morning.
It feels good.
What do you say we take a
little walk before heading home?
YUKI ONNA: I'd love to.
RIKUO: Hey, Yuki
Onna, how old are you?
YUKI ONNA: Huh?
Well--
RIKUO: Oh, was it something
I shouldn't have asked?
[crying]
RIKUO: Uh, don't cry.
I'm sorry.
YUKI ONNA: Next time,
"Red Plum Blossoms
on the Demon's Mountain."