[theme music]
-They've finally arrived.
-Yes, it seems so,
Supreme Commander.
-Hm?
TSURARA: "The Moon
is in the Sky."
-What is this power?
It's so strong.
[growling]
-I'll take care of this.
-Get back, Shoei.
-You're in no
condition to fight.
A commander puts his life
on the line, doesn't he?
-Come on let's get going.
-Hey, where are all the yokai?
-Huh?
Kiyotsugu.
-Hey, Ienaga, Yura,
you're already here.
YURA: Where were you guys?
IENAGA: We were
trying to reach you.
-In any case, I'm glad
you two could join us.
Now where are all the yokai?
Have you seen any around here?
There are countless posts on
the Kiyojuji Paranormal Patrol
Homepage about yokai
sightings in this area.
Hey, yokai, where are you?
Hey!
-Finally, there are no more
weak and pathetic fools
left to interrupt us.
We can fight to our hearts'
content-- Fear against Fear.
-I'm afraid I don't
know of any fools.
I have comrades though.
-Anyone who stands at the
top has no need for comrades.
I will be the Lord of
Isolation and reign over
the corpses of all yokai.
-Your eyes are blinded by
arrogance, but I'll fix that.
-Anyone who dares look down on
me cannot be allowed to exist
in this world.
-Over there.
Master Rikuo!
-Look at that class
of yokai aura.
-It's unbelievable.
In all my years, I've never
seen a battle like this.
-This is amazing.
-Master.
Kejoro.
-If I were you, I'd have
faith in the man I love.
-Hey, are you seeing
yokai over there?
-Wait, don't go.
-Why not?
-Because what's happening
is way over our heads.
Just forget it.
-Well, If an onmyoji herself
says so, who am I to argue?
-Do you think that he'll be OK?
-I don't know.
It's a fight between
two monsters.
-Yeah, but I don't think
of him as a monster at all.
He's different.
-Still, he's a bona fide
yokai, you can't deny that.
-But if he goes out of
his way to protect humans,
doesn't that mean he must
have a heart like a human?
-Absolutely.
We cannot rule out the existence
of yokai who have feelings like
humans do, and who
are our allies.
After all, not that long
ago, my own young life
was saved by a
yokai such as that.
-Oh yeah, that's
right, Kiyotsugu.
-Though it's
doubtful you actually
saw yokai since you
were half asleep.
[grumble]
-I'm sure you'll get
to see one some day.
-So I guess that means
that even among yokai,
there are some monsters who have
lost their hearts and others
who haven't.
-That's right.
-You're a stubborn one.
-It's morning.
-Not good.
Dawn is starting to break.
-Master will be
at a disadvantage.
-This is terrible.
Once the sun rises, Master
Rikuo will transform.
-He'll revert back
into his Day form.
-Do not fear, Rikuo.
There is a moon even
in broad daylight.
It simply goes unnoticed.
But the moon is
always in the sky,
and it always exists
deep inside of you.
-If you can't dodge the next
one, the wound will be fatal.
-Rikuo, after you defeated me,
you became the strongest yokai
in the Nura Clan.
Night and Day.
Embrace them both, and you will
become the Lord of Pandemonium.
-I will not lose.
All my friends are
depending on me.
-And these friends of yours,
are they human or yokai?
Which are they?
Don't tell me you're going
to save both, aren't you?
That silly idea of yours
is what makes you weak.
Well, I'll take those
friends of yours
and make them part
of my Night Parade.
-Damn it.
What the hell's going on there?
-Maybe we should
try and help him?
-Just how do you propose
we help Master Rikuo
without getting in the way?
-I hate to admit
it, but he's right.
There's nothing much we
can do at this point.
-Don't mess with me.
-I saw cherry blossoms.
-Really?
-Wait, I don't see anything
like that over there.
-Master.
-Night or Day, it
doesn't matter.
You and I are one.
And we're going to protect
both humans and yokai, right?
-Right.
-Heh heh.
And now, Rikuo Nura,
this is the moment
when you become part of my
Night Parade of 100 Demons.
Huh?
What-- what happened?
-Don't you know, Tamazuki, about
the moon out in broad daylight?
-What?
-There's a moon in
the morning sky.
-Where did you go?
What's happening?
-What is going on?
-It's there.
I can see it.
-Yes, I can see clearly now too.
-That is, without a doubt,
a flurry of cherry blossoms.
-You know, I can feel my
blood starting to boil.
-Shut the hell up!
What?
I just cut you down, so how
can you still be standing?
-Kyoka Suigetsu.
-Another one of
Nurarihyon's techniques.
It doesn't matter.
I am the one who
surpassed my father.
Inugamigyoubu Tanuki!
-It's not your father
you need to surpass.
The only person you need to
overcome here is yourself.
[screaming]
-Tamazuki!
-No, my hunter demons,
they're leaving me.
My powers are fading.
Stop!
[groaning]
-How could this be?
-It's all over.
-Ah, just in time.
-Gramps?
-Couldn't have cut
it much closer.
-Master Rikuo.
-Enough, Tamazuki.
Stop this immediately.
-Supreme Commander.
[interposing voices]
-Is everybody all right?
TAMAZUKI: I see.
it-- it wasn't enough.
Only when I stand
atop the corpse
of my weakening of a father,
will the Devil's Blade
manifest its true power!
-What the--?
-Oh no.
[gasp]
RIKUO: Some yokai choose
to follow your Fear,
and yet you betrayed them.
You should at least take
care of ones who admire you.
-That yokai.
-He's huge.
-You blithering idiot.
You are such a foolish son.
-Please, father, put me down.
-I beg you all,
please, forgive my son.
He may have transgressed, but
he's still a dear son of mine.
I will see to it that he
makes amends for his behavior.
[alarm clock]
RIKUO: Oh no, what time is it?
-Rikuo, are you awake?
I'm coming in.
Good morning.
-Oh, morning, mom.
I overslept.
I have to get to school.
-Master.
-Huh?
Yuki Onna.
-It's Sunday morning.
There isn't any school
on the weekends.
Besides, you're in no
condition to go anywhere.
-Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
-Do you realize you slept
for two straight days, Master
Rikuo?
-Good morning, Natto Kozo.
-Well, according
to Zen, you should
be making a full
recovery in no time.
Oh, I'm not finished
doing the laundry.
Can you two look
after him for me?
BOTH: OK.
-Master.
-Jeez, mom is so
energetic, isn't she?
-Yes, and Lady Wakana's
smile is very reassuring too.
Even that morning, when
she saw us in shambles,
she greeted us all
with a warm smile.
NATTO KOZO: Master,
the Supreme Commander
asked if you would go
see him once you're awake
and feel up to it.
RIKUO: OK.
I'll be right there.
NATTO KOZO: Oh, but don't
force yourself to get up.
RIKUO: It's better if
I move around a little.
-Are you sure, Master?
-You know, if you
worry too much,
your natto will spill out.
-Uwah.
-So?
-Oh, uh, what do you mean?
-Well, there's Day
and Night Master,
and the other Master
from that morning.
Who is the one that
you really like?
-I don't understand.
What are you trying to say?
-Oh my I can't believe
how much you're blushing.
You have such a pure heart
for someone your age.
-You didn't have to add
"for someone your age."
But yes, that morning, Master
Rikuo was absolutely divine.
-OK, OK, stop drooling.
-That old coot Inugamigyoubu
Tanuki and his,
uh-- what was his
son's name again?
-Tamazuki.
-Oh yes, yes,
Tamazuki, that's right.
It seems they returned
home to Shikoku safely.
-I see.
-That old Tanuki.
You know, he was prepared to
see his son died that day.
In fact, he expected it.
However, you put down your
sword without delivering
the finishing blow.
He told me he will never
forget the compassion
that you showed him.
And then he promised
he would do all
he could to instill that
same compassion in his son.
[slapping]
[dog panting]
[barking]
-Hm?
What are you doing?
Are you planning on
following me around?
What an odd little fellow.
I'm never going to
spoil you, you know?
[bark]
-And so this incident has
been settled by Master Rikuo
while striking a bargain
with the Shikoku Yokai,
and is officially over.
-What's that?
He struck a bargain?
Shoei, what are you doing?
SHOEI: Sit down.
You're in the way.
-Hey there, Hitotsume.
-Uh, hi.
-OK, thanks for waiting.
-We have all looked forward to
seeing you, Supreme Commander
and Master Rikuo.
-Welcome home, Master.
-Yes, welcome home, Master.
RIKUO: Thank you.
Thank you very much, everyone.
-A toast to the debut of
Master Rikuo's own Night Parade
and the prosperity
of the Nura Clan.
Huh?
Hm.
Cheers!
ALL: Cheers!
-Here you go, Yuki.
Drink up.
You know, whenever I'm
at a critical point,
I like to think back to the time
when I fought against at Mt.
Nejireme.
GYUKI: You had reached a
measure of self-realization
even before that time.
You just hadn't accepted it yet.
RIKUO: You're right.
I know now that
I'm always myself,
whether it's night or day.
-Yes, that you are.
You have both sides in you,
which is why you're strong.
-I really feel like dancing now.
-Now you're talking.
Let's see some of your moves.
-Well then, I think
I'm going to dance too.
-Go for it, Rikuo.
-Heh, it always
ends up like this.
These guys are so lame.
-You say that, but I'll bet
you're itching to join in,
are you, Gozu?
-Don't be ridiculous.
-Ow.
-Well, you two, it seems your
wounds have all healed up.
-It's only going to get
tougher for the Nura Clan.
Without a doubt, your strength
will become essential to us.
-We're counting on you.
-Hmph.
-And at that moment, in order to
protect the Supreme Commander,
I caught one Shikoku
yokai after another,
tearing them up
and tossing them--
-All right, everyone,
time to go inside and eat.
ALL: OK.
-Huh?
-I thought it would be
much wiser to send them
to the dojo instead of
letting them wander.
Oh.
-Great, why today of all days?
-Yoo hoo.
-Hi, Nura.
-We came by for a visit.
-It seems very lively
at your house today.
-Uh, yeah, some of my
relatives are over.
-As usual, this place
reeks with yokai aura.
-Your relatives?
-Ah.
-Wha--?
-Huh?
What is it?
What's the matter, Shima?
Hm?
-It's nothing.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-What?
-Rikuo, I'm curious, are you--?
YURA (VOICEOVER): What?
Is Ienaga going to kiss him in
front of everyone this time?
-You do, you look
like him a little.
Sort of.
-Like who?
-Hm.
NARRATOR: Rikuo Nura, the
young master of the Nura Clan
that claims 10,000 yokai
followers across the country.
The day he will take over
as the Third Heir may not
be so far away.
NARRATOR: Tamazuki's ambition
is brought to an end.
Some of the yokai returned
home, while many others
returned to the heavens.
As for Rikuo--
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Next time--
"The Afterglow of Youth."