NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
Demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Rikuo awakens
to his Yokai form,
rescuing his friends
from certain doom.
But things were far from over.
The premonition of danger
still lingered in the air.
-So, you finally decided.
-Then we will put our lives on
the line to fulfill your wish.
The death of the third heir.
GIRL: Red Plum Blossoms
on the Demon's Mountain.
-Ienaga, I'm sorry.
For putting you
through that nightmare.
If only I was stronger,
I could've protected you.
-Mm-mm.
It's not your fault, Yura.
Don't worry about it.
And besides, I was
definitely afraid of Yokai
before, but that man.
He was different.
He was there to save us both.
Maybe there are Yokai
who aren't scary.
YURA (VOICEOVER):
Being saved by a Yokai.
What a disgrace for an Onmyoji.
Some day, I will redeem myself.
-Oh, here you guys are!
-Kiyotsugu just called.
The Kiyojuji Paranomal
Patrol is having a meeting.
-Good.
Looks like everyone's here.
I have a huge
announcement to make.
-What sort of announcement?
-What is it?
Tell us.
-You'll love this, guy's.
This weekend, we, the Kiyojuji
Paranormal Patrol, will--
-Huh?
One of our members
seems to be missing.
-Huh?
Where is Nura?
Master?
Oh, my!
Now that I think of it, I
haven't seen the Master all day
today!
-It's so cold.
-Natto Kozou, When you're
done with the laundry,
gather some medicinal
herbs for the Master.
-Gotcha.
You go hurry and take
that water to the Master.
-You still have a
pretty high fever.
You should try and get
a little more sleep.
-OK.
-I brought you some cold water.
-Thank you, Kubinashi.
-Hey, Zen.
-I can't believe how pathetic
you are during the day.
You overdo it a little
and you get a fever?
-Look who's talking.
You're more sickly than I am.
-So, is it true that
you really don't
remember the fight you had?
-Well, I, um--
-That's too bad.
I really want the
Rikuo that came out
that night to become
the third heir.
I'm going now.
Take care, Rikuo.
-Master!
I'm so sorry.
I'm supposed to be
your closest aid,
and yet I didn't notice that
you never came to school today.
I spent the whole day
completely unaware!
Punish me in whatever
way you see fit.
[screaming]
-I believe that Kyuso was hired
by someone to cause this mess.
Someone who definitely
does not want Master Rikuo
to become the third heir.
-It's well known that Rikuo has
reawakened as a Yokai again.
It must be someone
who is not pleased
with the new development.
-Gyuki, what do you think?
-The Master thoroughly
defeated Kyuso.
There is no doubting his
formidable skills as a Yokai.
However, the simple fact
remains that he can only
maintain that state for
a quarter of the day
at the very most.
We must wait and
see how he develops.
For now, we should
talk about this matter
slowly and carefully.
-Hmph.
Acting all goody goody, huh?
-This'll do the trick.
It's my special ice compress.
It'll make your
fever go away fast.
Now I'm gonna get you some
medicine, so just relax 'til
I get back.
-It's heavy.
Tsurara, There's
way too much ice.
Can you melt it
down a little bit?
KANA: Huh?
Tsurara?
-Huh?
Kana!
-Ienaga isn't alone.
We all decided to come too!
-Hey there.
-Hello.
-Why are you guys all here?
-Well, isn't that obvious?
We came to see how
you're feeling, Nura.
You're pathetic.
Only fools catch cold.
-Well, I guess
I'll excuse myself.
-Thank you, Miss Housekeeper.
Goodbye.
-Say, Rikuo, did you just
mistake me for someone else?
-Huh?
What do you mean?
I think you called me Tsurara.
-Oh, are you all right, Rikuo?
Have you taken any medicine?
-No, not yet.
-Wait right here and relxas.
I'll go get some for you.
If I'm not mistaken, the
kitchen is this way, right?
I'll be back in a minute.
-No, Kana, wait a second.
-Uh, Oikawa?
-Ienaga?
-Huh?
-W--what are you doing here?
TSURARA (VOICEOVER):
Calm down, Yuki Onna.
Don't even think about
freezing them and wiping them
of the face of the earth.
-Uh, well, you see,
she's just here to--
-I get it.
You decided to come
visit and got here first.
-Yeah, yeah, that's it.
She got here just before
you about 10 minutes ago.
-Yeah, that's right, I did!
Ha ha!
OK.
Please get up now.
-Oikawa?
-Open wide.
-Thanks, Tsurara.
-No problem.
-I was right, then.
You did say Tsurara.
-OK, enough with
the nursemaid stuff.
Now that the Kiyojuji Paranormal
Patrol is all together
in one place, I want to announce
this weekend's big, exciting
schedule.
-This weekend?
-Yes.
You probably don't have
plans anyway, right?
Unlike me, who's so busy.
I've been in touch with an
expert on all things Yokai,
and we're gonna have the
privilege of meeting him
this weekend.
-Huh?
-Re you serious?
-And this Yokai expert has even
reserved rooms for all of us
at a wonderful inn.
A Yokai adventure!
-A what?
Should we go?
-I'm free this weekend,
so I don't mind going.
Kana?
-Me?
I, um--
-Well, it sounds to
me like it's going
to be a fun little outing.
Of course you're going
too, right Rikuo?
-Mm-hm.
If my fever goes down.
-Huh?
All right!
Yura has already
agreed to join me,
and I'm also counting
Nura and Oikawa in!
-I'll go too.
-Yeah, I'll be going too.
-What do you say?
You wanna go to?
-Yeah, let's go.
-OK, then we're set.
We'll be meeting our Yokai
expert at Ume Rakuen Garden.
That's where the Kiyojuji
paranormal patrol
will go for its first
Yokai field trip!
-I guess it's OK.
-Ume Rakuen, huh?
-Hey, Karasu Tengu.
-Yes?
-Go look into our
clan roster to see
if anyone was in
contact with Kyuso.
-You think there's
a traitor among us?
Very well, sir.
Then I'll dispatch my foolhardy
sons, the Sanba Garasu,
to investigate all this.
-I wonder what will turn up.
A demon or a snake.
[gurgling]
Now then.
I'm feeling a bit hungry.
I think I'll go find some
place I can eat for free.
-Rikuo and Oikawa.
Those two seemed really close.
What am I thinking?
[phone ringing]
-Rikuo?
Hello?
This is Kana.
-Um, about the
field trip tomorrow.
What would a normal girl usually
take to something like that?
-What do you mean by normal?
I mean, why do you need to know
something like that, Rikuo?
-Oh, uh, well--
-Not that it really matters.
-Let's see.
A change of clothes,
some night cream.
-Yeah, OK.
anything else?
-Hey, Master Rikuo.
Who are you talking
to over there?
-Uh, Rikuo.
That wasn't Oikawa's voice
I just heard, was it?
RIKUO (ON PHONE): Oh, no!
That was, um, uh,
just my mom talking.
Thanks a lot.
See you tomorrow.
-Here.
I hope this will
be enough for you.
-Thank you, Lady Wakana!
-By the way.
Where are you all going
for this field trip?
-Some place called Ume Rakuen.
-Doesn't it sounds like it's
going to be a lot of fun?
-Ume Rakuen?
-Have you been there before?
-Mm-mm.
But I think I've heard
the name somewhere.
I'm sure was nothing.
Anyway, have fun, you two.
-OK!
-Good.
Now then.
Is everybody ready to do this?
-Mm-hm.
-Right then, let's do.
Ready, set!
Dammit, it's Natto Kozou again!
-Man, Nura won again.
You've got an awful lot of
luck with Yokai, don't you?
How can anyone win
20 consecutive times
in Yokai poker?
It's just sheer
coincidence, really.
Oh!
Master is the future leader
of all the Yokai after all.
Even in a Yokai card game,
he naturally takes the lead.
KANA (VOICEOVER): There she goes
again, giving Rikuo that look.
What's the deal between them?
-Are there really
Yokai at Ume Rakuen?
-Master.
I, Aotabo, will
accompany you everywhere
you go to the ends of the Earth.
-How many times do we
have to transfer trains?
-My back hurts.
-OK, everyone!
Take a look.
There's our destination.
-Wow.
The plum blossoms
are still in bloom.
SAORI: It's beautiful.
-I thought that this
was gonna be a garden,
but it's a mountain.
-All right now.
Don't worry about
the small stuff.
Let's go.
First we're meeting up
with a Yokai professor
at Umewakamaru Shrine!
-A shrine?
-Which way is it?
-I don't know.
We're just gonna have to
find it for ourselves.
It's somewhere on this mountain.
-What?
We have to search
the whole mountain?
[sigh]
-I don't sense any Yokai energy,
but I can't let my guard down.
-Oikawa!
You want me to carry
your backpack for you?
-No, it's all right.
Wow, it's beautiful.
It's almost like a
paradise, isn't it?
I'm so glad we came.
Well, let's get going, shall we?
-Oh, man.
It's all mountain.
-My feet hurt.
Are you sure this is
the meeting place?
-Yeah.
There doesn't seem
to be anyone here.
-Oh, come on, don't
be stupid, Shima.
It's because there aren't
people here that Yokai appear,
probably.
-Probably, huh?
-I'd rather they didn't appear.
-Master?
-Hey, what is that over here?
-What are you talking about?
-It's a small shrine, and
I think a jizo statue.
-Where?
-It's hard to see
from here, but there's
something written on it,
I'll go and check it out.
-It says Umewakamaru.
-How can you see that?
-Well, Miss Keikain?
-Wow.
You're right.
-This is the shrine
we've been looking for!
Isn't it great?
We did it, Yura!
-Is that--
-Yes, I'm afraid so.
this mountain really may
have some lurking about.
YURA (VOICEOVER): I
feel something ominous.
-Who's that filthy looking man?
-Don't be stupid.
He's the writer and
Yokai researcher,
Professor Adashibara.
-Hey, you guys found
the Umewakamaru shrine
pretty quickly.
Good job, Kiyojuji
paranormal patrol.
-I'm very honored to meet you.
-Yes.
Um, who is this Umewakamaru
that's enshrined here?
-Umewakamaru is the hero
of the ancient Yokai
legend about this mountain and
the creatures who inhabit it.
-A Yokai legend?
-Follow me.
-Would you mind repeating
that, my foolhardy sons?
-It's just deciding, that's all.
It doesn't mean he's
behind all this yet.
But the crows of Ukiyoe
Town were watching.
-I see.
-What is that?
What is all this?
-Those, miss, are claws.
-Claws?
-The Yokai live right up
here on this mountain.
You can't let a mere
torn off claw scare you.
-Yes!
I knew it.
I knew this mountain
would have Yokai on it.
-Oh no.
What are we gonna do
if one really appears?
-And the best part is that the
hero of this mountain's Yokai
legend, Umewakamaru is up there.
-I simply can't believe that
he would actually do that.
-Rikuo isn't coming home today?
-No, he's gone on an
outing with his club.
-Karasu Tengu, why don't
you join me for some tea?
-Yes.
I'd really like that.
-So, where did Rikuo
and his friends go?
-He said they were all
going to Ume Rakuen.
-They went to Ume Rakuen, eh?
Well, I think that's
a great place.
-Oh, so you've
been there before?
-But Supreme Commander.
That mountain is-- No,
no I can't linger here.
-Hey!
Foolhardy sons of mine!
-Master.
-See, many ages ago, Ume Rakuen
was known by another name.
-Why was that?
-People believed that a Yokai
who attacks lost travelers
lived on this mountain.
The rumors spread, and
pretty soon, people
began to avoid the area.
In order to quell all the
fear and put the rumor
to rest once and for all,
the hopeful residents
began calling this place a
paradise of plum blossoms.
Its original name was Mt.
Nejireme.
-Master.
That means--
-That's right.
The Yokai who lives on Mt.
Nejireme is him.
It's Gyuki.
-The prey has come
to the mountain.
-I knew I had heard
of Ume Rakuen before.
I just hadn't made
the connection.
I've always known it as Mt.
Nejireme, the mountain
where Gyuki lives.
I hope Gyuki will be happy
to see Rikuo and his friends.
-I'm most certain that he will
warmly welcome all of them.
-So, it seems it was Gyuki
who was manipulating Kyuso
after all.
I'll just sit back
and watch you at work.
-Master.
NARRATOR: Mt.
Nejireme.
A dark, mysterious
mountain where
a frightening Yokai who devours
lost travellers resides.
[theme music]
MAN: You're standing out
from the other students, Ao.
AOTABO: Why?
I'm dressed like any
middle schools would be.
MAN: Actually, I think
I'd look better in it.
AOTABO: Wait, you wanna
wear a school uniform?
MAN: Uh--
NARRATOR: Next time, A Trap
is Set on the Evil Mountain.