NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The who stood at the helm and
led the Night Parade of 100
Demons was known as the
supreme commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium, Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: For the Nura
clan and its third heir,
Rikuo Nura, a long, fierce
night was about to begin.
-I'll go in first and
distract the enemy,
then you guys go
in for the attack.
-I will keep Master Rikuo safe.
-Just leave all those who are
wounded in battle to my care.
-We'll meet you
guys there after we
take care of things on our end.
-Sounds good.
-A hazy moon.
Looks like it's going
to be a long night.
As long as that
moon is visible, I
want you to entrust
your lives to me.
ALL: Yeah!
GIRL (VOICEOVER):
Darkness And Ice.
-Hurry up, Mezu.
You've got to keep up with me.
-I know.
I am.
KANA: Something wrong, Yura?
-Oh, it's nothing.
This feels so good.
I haven't had a chance to
relax in a bathtub for a while.
-It's rough being an
Onmyoji, isn't it?
-Yeah.
And I'm still in training.
Ienaga, why didn't you run when
that suspicious looking guy
started talking to you?
-Because he reminded
me of another person.
But he turned out to
be nothing like him.
The person I know
is really scary,
but he makes me feel safe.
That guy, Tamazuki,
was very different.
He was really creepy.
Just thinking about him
makes me sick to my stomach.
That's why I was really happy
when you came to my rescue,
and then you said you'd
come over and spend
the night with me.
-Ienaga, this person
you keep talking of--
is he the same Yokai
who saved us that day?
-Mm-hm.
-I knew it.
I'd better get out.
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
BOY: This was the one
thing I didn't want to do.
Everyone?
-Huh?
-We brought all
of you some food.
Being disguised as a girl
is so damn embarrassing.
Stupid Gozumaru.
-I'm in disguise, too.
-You call thing a disguise?
-This is the best I can do.
-So, did Lord Tamazuki hire you
to bring us some provisions?
You're pretty cute
up close, you know?
-Oh, really?
-Wow.
There are so many of you.
Got to hand it to Lord Tamazuki.
-Well, he is the one
who got his hands
on the Legacy of the Conqueror.
-The Legacy of the Conqueror?
-You're absolutely right.
-With the devil's blade
in his possession,
a Shikoku victory is certain.
MAN: The enemy is coming!
Get ready!
-What?
Let's go grab a drink
after the fight.
[nervous laughter]
-The devil's blade, huh?
-Now hold it, Gozumaru.
You're not gonna--
-This Legacy of
the Conqueror seems
to be the source of
Tamazuki's power, right?
Let's steal it, then impress
the guys back at the main house.
-I knew it.
-Now's our chance.
[crash]
-Huh?
-I hate guys who
are too talkative.
So I thought I'd teach them a
lesson in manners using this.
BOY: Summon the devil?
-And in just a
moment, the two of you
will feel the power
of this blade, too.
I've been expecting
you, Rikuo Nura!
[laughter]
How nice.
You have the eyes
of a challenger
who doesn't know his own limits.
However, that's all
going to end here.
Now behold, the
power of Tamazuki!
-Look at Lord Tamazuki!
-He's transformed
into his Yokai form!
-You mean that's his true form?
-The time has come
to realize my dream.
In the name of 88
demons of Shikoku,
I shall now take your
life, and your fear,
as I promised you I would.
-Are you done
talking now, Tanuki?
-Yes!
The glory is all mine!
-I got this.
-Move it!
-Now, the great Battle of
the Night Parades will begin.
Go, my Yokai!
Go and lay down
your life for me!
-Let's go get him, everyone!
[shouting]
-Master!
What are you doing?
Please wait!
-Look, their
commander's all alone.
-We'll be heroes if we kill him.
TAMAZUKI (VOICEOVER):
Has he gone mad?
He's supposed to
be their commander.
-Rikuo Nura!
Hey Tamazuki, he's mine.
I'm tear him to pieces!
-Very well, Inugami.
Then bring me his head.
[shouting]
TAMAZUKI (VOICEOVER): He's
making himself an easy target.
What a fool.
I think this battle
will end very quickly.
-Follow Master Rikuo!
-I shall protect you, master!
-We'll go this way,
for a surprise attack!
Who's there?
-A Dance of the Black Weapons!
It turns out you're pretty
useful just sitting there
like that.
-Hold it.
Your opponent is
standing right here.
I guess you still haven't
learned your lesson, old lady?
Fine, then.
Let's settle this
right here and now.
-Take this.
Needle Hell!
-You'll have to do
better than that.
-Master?
Where'd he go?
[shouting]
-Pick on someone your own size.
Hurry up and go to Master Rikuo.
-Where are you?
Riko Nura!
Show yourself!
-Where is he?
-I can't say for
certain, but perhaps he's
already been killed
by one of our men.
-Lord Tamazuki, what is it?
-What are you all doing?
The enemy commander's
walking past you!
Why isn't anyone attacking?
Can they not see
him walking there?
-Hey.
-Huh?
Why are the two commanders
going head to head?
-I see.
Your presence
overwhelms your enemies
to the point where they
can't even see you anymore.
So this is the
fear you possess--
the power of Nurarihyon!
-Master!
-There you are, Rikuo Nura!
-I will not allow you to
get close to our master.
-Hold on, master.
I'm coming!
-Strawberry milk hits the
spot after a hot bath.
-Yokai.
-Um, hey, Yura?
What are you doing?
-Peanuts?
Don't tell me you and that Yokai
leader were in here eating?
-Huh?
Why in the world
would I do that?
I mean, I don't
even know who he is.
-Listen, I know you like
him, but he's bad news.
-Huh?
-Yokai will always be evil.
You'll only get yourself hurt.
-I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
But you know what?
That's something that I
need to find out for myself.
Please try to understand.
-I see.
[gasp]
-What's the matter?
-I don't believe this.
I've never sensed Such
massive Yokai aura.
I have to go.
Something terrible is
starting to happen out there.
[car horns]
-Aw.
What happened just now?
-I just got a case
of the chills.
-Tell me why we're
having club activities
in the park at night.
And I can't seem to
reach Kana, either.
-Well, the chances
of seeing Yokai
are a lot better at night.
-Hey.
What's the matter, Kiyotsugu?
-Wow, look at this, Shima.
-Huh?
-Lots of reports of Yokai
sightings in Ukiyoe Town!
-Amazing.
-What is this?
It's going so fast,
I can't read it.
-Hm?
-OK, let's go!
-Uh, go where?
You don't mean--
-Yes, that's right!
We're going on a Yokai
field trip to Ukiyoe Town!
[laughter]
-Heh, heh.
You were careless.
Now, you shall learn the
power of those who follow me.
-What is this?
My eyes!
TAMAZUKI: Get him!
-Meikyo Shisui Sakura!
-What--
[screaming]
TAMAZUKI: Impressive,
Rikuo Nura.
However, that's
as far as you go.
-It's dark.
I can't see a thing.
TAMAZUKI: The principals of yin
and yang exist in this world.
That is to say, there
is darkness and light.
The darkness signifies Yokai.
We make ourselves disappear
into the darkness.
We are the shadows of the world.
Light signifies humans.
They live in the sunlight
and fear the darkness.
Light dispels darkness, and
the darkness devours light.
In other words, it's
impossible for humans and Yokai
to exist at the same time.
And so your existence
too is not possible.
Abandon the light and come
into the world of darkness.
Then you will finally
become a complete being.
This world has become
far too bright,
but together, you and I
can fill it with darkness.
Let me ask you,
Rikuo Nura, won't you
become part of my 88
demons of Shikoku?
-I refuse.
Light is radiant because
there is darkness.
And darkness is sublime
because there is light.
-I see.
What a shame.
Then I'll just kill you!
-I can't see.
I'm being swallowed
by the darkness.
-You will not lay a hand on him.
-What is this?
It's cold.
It's like the time
when I was little.
(CHILD'S VOICE) I was
playing in the garden,
and before I knew it, everything
turned black around me.
I couldn't see a thing.
Except in one spot, skin
as white a snow stood out.
-So here you are, Master.
Master, snap out of it!
-Such impudence.
Prepare to die!
-This way.
-Yuki Onna.
You idiot.
Stay back.
This is between me and him.
-It's your eyes, isn't it?
-Just stay back!
-Stop trying to act so tough!
You would be lying
dead right now
if I hadn't shown
up to save you.
You are so exasperating.
Listen up!
I'm your opponent now!
-No.
Get out.
-Rikuo Nura's guardian.
You can show us just how
loyal you really are.
Get her.
-Run away, Yuki Onna.
That Yokai's Yosuzume.
-Huh?
This is Yosuzume
MAN: It's pitch black!
MAN: What is this?
-What?
-I can't see a thing.
-So, here you are, Master.
I was worried about you.
I thought you came into
contact with Yosuzume.
-Yosuzume?
-That's right.
I've heard that the feather
of the Yokai known as Yosuzume
can slip into the eye through
the tiniest of openings
and create total darkness
for whoever encounters him.
-Is that the best of
your so-called loyalty?
Pathetic.
Your guardian is useless.
-Yosuzume.
Show them what
you can really do.
-It's awfully quiet
all of the sudden.
What is that?
Gozumaru?
Mezumaru?
What happened?
Take them to Lord Zen.
-OK.
-Yuki Onna, run!
-Rikuo Nura.
it's time for the
curtain to fall.
TAMAZUKI: It's his fear.
Dammit.
He's disappearing again.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
What is that sword?
-Yuki Onna.
Is that you there?
-Yes.
I'm behind you.
-I thought I told
you to run away.
-Yeah, like I would
ever do such a thing.
I shall protect you forever.
I pledged my complete
and total loyalty to you.
-All right then, Yuki Onna.
You cover my back.
-Yes, sir.
You can count on me.
I'm going to stop Yosuzume's
Yokai spell of darkness.
-What do you think you can
do in your sorry state?
Go, Yosuzume!
Finish them off!
-She froze her left eye.
The feather didn't penetrate?
RIKUO: Stop!
Yosuzume!
-I've been waiting
for this exact moment.
Gather and freeze, my minions.
A cold greeting for
otherworldly guests.
Shine white in all the darkness.
Tremble in fear before
this freezing wind!
Cursed blizzard.
Chilling wind!
-I can see.
My sight's back again.
-Oh wow.
I actually did it!
Master Rikuo!
-Not bad, Yuki Onna.
Well, looks like it's
the beginning of act two.
[theme music]
KIYOTSUGU: Hey
Oikawa, What do you
think of these Yokai
playing cards I designed?
TSURARA: Wow.
It has all the Yokai's
power and techniques listed.
KIYOTSUGU: I'm also planning
to add their age as well.
TSURARA: I don't think you
need to write their age
KIYOTSUGU: Huh?
NARRATOR: Next time,
The Devil's Blade.