-In days of old,
people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the helm
and led the Night Parade of 100
demons was known as the
Supreme Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name for him.
The Lord of Pandemonium.
Nurarihyon.
[theme music - in japanese]
-Supreme Commander!
Supreme Commander
please, answer me!
Where are you?
Where have you gone,
Supreme Commander?
Supreme Commander!
-Oh, boy.
I hope this doesn't turn
into something really bad.
-Yeah.
Me too.
-Thank you for the food.
Huh?
-Huh?
[crying]
-He's not here either.
The Supreme Commander is gone.
[sigh]
-He wouldn't be in
there, of all places.
-He's right.
You'll never find him in there.
-Oh, Supreme Commander.
Where have you gone off to?
I'm so worried about you!
-Now, calm down, Karasu Tengu.
-Yes.
Don't worry.
Father always
disappears suddenly,
often for days at a time,
then shows up again.
-I know, but how
could he do this now?
Where could he possibly
go at a time like this?
Supreme Commander, come
out wherever you are.
Come out, please!
[sigh]
-Watch me.
I'll gather more fear than you
could ever hope to dream of.
[grunt]
-We finally arrived
at the place where
all our dreams can be fulfilled.
-Tell me.
Is it true that
Nurarihyon has gone
missing after battling Muchi?
-Yes.
We will take
advantage of the chaos
to destroy the Nura
clan in one blow.
[laughter]
-Still, the Nura clan
has within its ranks
many strong and
distinguished warriors.
Surely it won't be that easy.
-Ha.
They're nothing.
-Another thing to consider
is that Tochigami,
the deities of this region,
are the ones who actually
gather the people's
faith and fear.
The humans have developed
a deep bond with them
over a long period of time.
Because of that,
these deities can
be considered a valuable
asset to the Nura clan.
-Then the first thing
we do is wipe out
each and every one of them.
And then watch the Nura
clan's foundation crumble.
[laughter]
-Mere local deities.
Let them attack in droves.
I'll crush them one by
one with my own hands.
-This will be such
an easy conquest.
-You're right about that.
[laughter]
-All right.
I think it's time we all
went on a little rampage
through Ukiyoe Town, and create
a little diversion to lure
in their strongest fighters.
[laughter]
[loud shout]
[screaming]
-I didn't realize
how late it was.
-Mmm.
I have to hurry home
before my dad gets mad.
[gasps]
-What's going on?
[laughter]
-S-- someone help!
-What?
What's the matter?
-There's no mistaking it.
Yokai.
-Damn it.
Who the hell are these guys?
-They've got some nerve
coming here and storming
our territory.
What do you think they're up to?
-At this rate, it'll
turn into a war.
-They spell trouble.
-It could be them.
The Shikoku Yokai.
The Seven Phantom Travelers.
-The Seven Phantom Travelers?
-That name sounds familiar.
-They're Yokai who
represent Shikoku.
-Could they be the ones
who killed Lord Hihi?
-I'm not sure, but--
-Well, it certainly
is a possibility.
-Fortunately for us,
the humans are still
unaware that Yokai are behind
this latest disturbance.
-We must hurry and do something.
-So what's our plan, Master?
-Say, did you hear?
The Shikoku Yokai have shown
up and are running amok
all over town.
-I heard, I heard.
They're not ordinary Yokai.
They're just
incorrigible brutes.
-Yeah, a bunch of hooligans.
-But why are they doing this?
-Isn't it obvious?
They plan to take
over our territory.
-Ah!
-Take over?
-Yeah, and if they
succeed, it'll
spell the end of the Nura clan.
-Ahhh!
-Making such a fuss over some
Yokai bumpkins from Shikoku.
-Yeah.
Unlike the Gyuki
clan, this place
is full of good-for-nothings.
-How sad to think that
they're the main family.
-That's for sure.
-What'll happen to us?
-You guys'll
probably end up being
sliced up and served as sashimi.
-Oh, no!
-Oh, where's the Supreme
Commander when we need him?
-Come on, everyone.
Calm down.
The Nura clan's going
to be absolutely fine.
After all, we have someone
very special on our side.
-Oh, really?
Who is it?
-Aotabo or maybe Kurotabo?
-Ha.
The Master.
Who else would I
be talking about?
As long as we have
Master Rikuo, there's
absolutely nothing to fear,
-Hmm.
-Well, I suppose.
If you say so.
Right?
-Uh-- well, yes.
What a relief.
I guess.
-Yes.
Of course.
Thank goodness.
-Yes, it is.
Just trust me.
So let's not all jump to a
bunch of silly conclusions,
and just stick to carrying
out our chores like always.
OK?
Hmm?
(VOICEOVER) Still, I can't
help but worry a little.
What's going to happen to us?
Hmm.
-I wonder.
Are those Shikoku Yokai serious
about taking over our clan?
Gyuki.
-Quite a predicament, isn't it?
This is when your worth to the
Nura clan as the third heir
will be called into question.
[sigh]
-Tread carefully.
-Hmm.
-Master!
Are you sure about this?
Considering what's
going on, I don't
think you should be
leaving the house.
-There's no telling
what may happen.
It's dangerous for
you to be outside.
-The enemy is trying
to agitate us.
It's important that
we don't panic,
because that's what
they want us to do.
[sigh]
-So we need to keep on living
our lives just like we always
do.
And wait until the enemy
shows us their true colors.
-Master.
-Understood.
[bells ringing]
-Hey, guys!
Come over here.
You've all got to
check this out.
-Yokai are behind Ukiyoe
Town's calamities?
-Wha-- what is this?
-Countless posts about
the mysterious accidents
and calamities
that have occurred
all Ukiyoe Town since yesterday.
And nearly all of them say
that they witnessed Yokai.
-Really?
This is scary.
-So we're talking
about Yokai again?
Don't you ever get tired?
[laughter]
-I don't believe it!
You guys still don't understand
how serious all of this is,
do you?
There are even a bunch of
very detailed posts talking
about indisputable sightings
of the infamous Shikoku Yokai,
otherwise known as the
Seven Phantom Travelers.
Can't refute that, can you?
Huh?
Well, can you?
-Who are the Seven
Phantom Travelers?
-The Seven Phantom Travelers
are the most powerful and feared
Yokai group in Shikoku.
The story goes that anyone who
sees them on a mountain road
will not return to
their village alive.
[gasp]
-Village?
What era is that story from?
-You don't understand
anything, do you?
You don't get it at all!
-It's kind of scary how
those accidents took place
all at once.
Do you think it's a coincidence?
Or was a Yokai really
behind all of it?
Those Yokai.
-Everyone was talking
about the incident.
-Yeah.
-I just hope that nothing more
like that happens tonight.
-It'll be OK.
I told everyone to
keep their eyes open
and be extra vigilant.
-Pathetic humans.
With the coming of
night, terror and chaos
shall descend upon you.
Ah!
[shouting and screaming]
-What was that?
Come on, Yura.
-Get back!
-What?
But--
-I'll be fine.
Go!
-Her shikigame and onmyoji, eh?
She'll make a sufficient foe.
-I'll take you on.
-Caw!
-He's a fire-wielder.
-I'm not averse to feisty girls.
Caw!
-Yura!
[growl]
-Hold it.
-What?
-You must deal with us.
-Prepare yourself.
-Who are you?
-We are the Nura clan.
Sanba Garasu!
-Yura!
Are you all right?
-Yes.
It's just a minor burn.
[theme music]
-What?
Miss Kakine was injured?
-Yes.
In the park on the
way home from school.
I think it was a Yokai.
It suddenly attacked
us from the sky.
But we were saved.
-Huh?
-I don't know, but I'm pretty
sure our rescuers were also
Yokai.
They looked like a group
of really big black birds.
-Black birds?
Crows?
-Yes, like crows.
-I see.
-Rikuo You know I-- I think,
maybe, that Yokai really do
exist.
[gasp]
-So please, Rikuo.
Be very careful.
-Um, yeah.
I sure will, Kana.
Hmm?
-The top officers are
gathering in the mansion.
They will likely expect some
answers from you, Rikuo.
-Hmm.
[whimpering]
-Please help me!
[growls and grunts]
-Back then, my Yokai blood
had awakened already.
But for a very long
time, I was in denial,
because I had lots of friends.
They were very
precious to me and I
wanted to be human
just like them.
But I also have a family
who are just as precious.
Just as important to me.
My Yokai family.
And that's why I
will never forgive
anyone who dares to try to
hurt my friends and family.
Human or Yokai.
Gyuki.
I'm not going to
run away anymore.
-Good work, everyone.
You fired a brilliant
opening round of fireworks.
And now the curtain has
risen on our next act.
The stage is our
enemy's headquarters.
The Nura clan's mansion.
[panting]
-Well, well, brothers.
I see you've all
come here as well.
-Cut the act.
You're the one that arranged
this assembly, didn't you?
-This is the most serious affair
since our clan was formed.
I did what was necessary.
Surely you're not complaining.
-Hmm.
-Damn it!
How long must we
waste our time here?
[gasps]
-Oh-- oh.
If it isn't Shoei.
How you've grown since
the last I saw you.
Back then, you were still--
-Forget that.
My old man was killed, remember?
-Yes.
Of course.
You have my condolences.
You're mad.
I know you feel.
And it really pains me.
Who could blame you for
wanting to exact revenge
on those who did this?
I would want the
same if I were you.
-Then let me go and do it.
Let me find my old man's
killers and make them pay.
-But in the absence of
the Supreme Commander,
we have no one to rely
on but that Master.
-Hmm.
-I don't care what
the Master thinks.
I will avenge my old man.
-Yes.
Well said, son of Hihi.
Spoken like a true
warrior of the clan.
You're such a refreshing
change from our weak Master.
Don't you all agree?
It's very reassuring.
[laughter]
-Lord Hitotsume has a big mouth
to match that big head of his.
-He's making things
difficult for the Master.
-But he does have a point.
We need Master Rikuo to
take decisive action soon.
-Yeah.
You're right about that.
-Mmm.
Huh?
Master!
-Huh?
-I kept you waiting.
Sorry.
-If it isn't Master Rikuo.
You're rather late,
don't you think?
-And you were awfully
early, Hitotsume.
Weren't you?
-This is a serious affair
for the whole family.
I dropped everything and
rushed over right away.
-Good.
Then listen to
what I have to say.
From now on, no one is to
take any unauthorized action.
You are not to act alone.
No matter what
happens, the Nura clan
will be united and
face the enemy as one.
Is that clear, Shoei?
You must not go out and seek
vengeance all by yourself.
-But, Master!
By all rights, this has
to be an eye for an eye!
-I don't blame you, Shoei.
You're his son.
-Shoei, I feel the
same way as you do.
And that's why we just can't
let anything or anyone split
us apart.
Don't you get it?
That's exactly what
the enemy wants.
If Hihi were here now, he
would say the same thing.
[grunt]
-In any case, there's only
one way to deal with all this.
The clan must remain
strong and unyielding.
And so-- And so-- I
will lead the clan
in my grandfather's absence!
[gasps]
-As the third heir
of the Nura clan.
-Master!
-Oh, yeah.
Now you're talking, Master.
-We're counting on you, Master.
-Master.
I will follow your command.
-Thank you, Shoei.
-However, even as
we speak, the enemy
is continuing to
attack our land.
You say we will
not yield, but what
specific strategy do you have?
-First of all, we will
tighten up security
throughout our territory.
You will all take
steps to do that.
-Ha.
A strategy neither
interesting nor amusing.
-You idiot.
You can't win a war
with only defense.
[shouts and screams]
[gasp]
-Hmm?
Oh, honey.
Why?
My honey.
-How could anyone do this?
-What happened here?
-What's that?
Intruder!
The enemy has
infiltrated the house.
It's over!
It's the end of the Nura clan!
-Be quiet!
That's enough.
Stop making such a big ruckus.
What's important is to
find the one who did this.
-Rikuo Nura.
I am going to take your life.
-Huh?
-Come back here!
-Master!
[growling]
[gasp]
[screeching]
[growling]
[panting]
-So.
We meet again, Rikuo Nura.
I've come to officially
offer my greetings.
-Your greetings?
-Yes.
That's correct.
(VOICEOVER) The Shikoku Yokai's
Seven Phantom Travelers,
led by the Inugamigyobu-Tanuki
Tamazuki, present themselves.
A bloody battle without
honor is about to begin.
[theme music - in japanese]
-Tsurara, is your
body as cold as snow?
-Yes, pretty much.
-Then if we held hands,
would I get frostbite?
-Oh, it's OK.
You get used to
it after a while.
See?
-Ah!
It's cold Tsurara.
-Next time, "Fierce
Fire and Sudden Rain."