NARRATOR: In days of
old, people feared Yokai.
The one who stood at the
helm, and led the night
parade of a hundred
demons was known
as the Supreme
Commander of the Yokai.
They had another name
for him, the Lord
of Pandemonium-- Nurarihyon.
[theme music]
-Tamazuki is like I
was when I was young,
trying everything he can to gain
power, and rule through fear.
He now leads a group of Yokai
known as the Seven Phantom
Travelers.
-Seven Phantom Travelers, eh?
-Among them is one
known as Inugami.
He is an especially violent
and dangerous Yokai.
-Inugami.
-Hate and malice
feeds his power.
Of all of them, he
is one to be feared.
NARRATOR: A dark force
threatens the lives
of Rikuo and his friends.
His name-- Inugamigyoubu
Tanuki Tamazuki.
He and the Seven Phantom
Travelers of Shikoku
have declared war against
the Nura Clan in an attempt
to take over their
territory before conquering
the whole country.
-That's enough.
-Long ago, I wanted to
fit in with human society,
so I tried desperately
to act like one of them.
WOMAN: What's with this guy?
He's scary.
GIRL: Eww.
What a creep.
MAN: Man, he's annoying.
-But they wouldn't accept me.
I spent my entire life being
ostracized, all because I
was born a Yokai
and not a human.
Back then, I wasn't even aware
that a world for Yokai existed.
I had no friends.
I was alone with nowhere
to go until that day.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): The
Curtain Falls in the Darkness.
-I hate you.
I hate you, Rikuo Nura!
I want to kill you now!
-Look.
His head.
-Die!
-They're coming after us!
-What do we do?
-Don't worry.
-Be careful.
-I'll clear them
out in one sweep.
Shikigami Rentei!
Shikigami Convert!
Jinshiki Synthesis!
Keikain Style Onmyo Jutsu,
Vanish to the Abyss.
Yura Max!
There are too many of them.
-I got the light bulb replaced.
-Yeah.
It seems to be working.
-What now?
-Right.
Back to the auditorium.
-Huh?
-The Yokai should
be appearing soon.
-But Kiyotsugu, what if Yokai
really do appear out there?
-Don't worry, Shima.
I've got everything
under control.
Remember I have this-- the Seven
Branched Sword of Exorcism!
-Oh no.
-It's out again!
-Master Rikuo,
are you all right?
-Yeah.
Thanks.
-How dare you interfere!
I won't miss this time!
-Master!
-Yuki Onna, no!
-Die!
What is this?
-That was close.
-You think you're so
damn smart, don't you?
But a string like
this is nothing.
-It's useless.
The more you struggle
to escape, the tighter
this string winds around you.
-Kubinashi's string,
isn't just for
-Bastard!
Damn it!
I can't move.
-On that day, I learned
for the first time
that Yokai had their own
society, just like humans.
-I want you to join,
and be part of my group.
After all, you're
a Yokai too, right?
-Join you?
If you want me to join
you, why would you do this?
Why?
Why do you have to put
me through all this crap?
-It's quite simple.
I want to see how strong you.
-How strong?
I'm not strong at all.
-Then do you want to die?
A weak Yokai simply
doesn't deserve to live,
because he'll only end up
being shunned and despised
instead of feared by humans.
Or do you want to go
back to your old life?
-No.
I don't.
And I don't want to die!
Damn it.
They're all the same.
I didn't ask to be this way!
[screaming]
-That was incredible.
The more your hatred
for humans builds,
the greater your power becomes.
-Come with me.
Let me show you.
Come and see the new
world of the Yokai.
-Tamazuki turned me, someone
who is neither human nor Yokai,
into a true Yokai with power!
-Tamazuki, leader of
the Shikoku Yokai.
-Tamazuki is the one who
inspires true fear, the one who
should rule over the Yokai.
Compared to him, you're nothing.
You waste your efforts trying
to blend in with the humans.
Even when he was among
the human society,
Tamazuki stood out as a leader.
He drew them in with
his power and charisma.
Unlike you who has his
guards to protect him,
and who chooses to play around
with his little human friends.
-Don't move.
-Inugami, listen to me.
You've been taken
in by Tamazuki.
-Ha.
Taken in?
Tamazuki is the sly
tanuki who doesn't
hesitate to put on
sheep's clothing.
I've known that from
the very beginning.
Still, Tamazuki is
the one who taught me
that Yokai stand above humans,
that I have power inside of me,
that there is a place for me.
He taught me all that.
-Then he taught you
something very wrong.
Yokai are no better or
worse than humans are.
-No!
He's not wrong!
-What?
What is that?
-Huh?
What's going on here?
-Hatred and anger have finally
awakened Inugami's true power,
making him unstoppable now.
[chuckling]
-He acknowledged me.
Tamazuki is the only
one in this entire world
who accepted me for what I am!
He's not wrong!
-No.
This is bad.
-I will not acknowledge you.
I'll never acknowledge
the existence of a Yokai
who is liked by everyone.
-It's useless.
My strings cannot be
broken that easily.
-Master, please step back.
-I am Tamazuki's loyal servant.
I am the Yokai, Inugami!
[roar]
-Aw.
It doesn't seem to be
working at all now.
Huh?
Hear that?
-What was it?
-It seems to be coming
from the auditorium.
Shima, go check it out, and
find out what's going on.
-Huh?
-I'm busy here trying to
get this darn projector
to work properly.
Who else is there to do it?
-All right.
I'll go check it out.
Cripes.
He's such a slave driver.
Was the screen always
torn like that?
[panicked gasping]
-Is this real?
It is real!
Kiyotsugu, it's here.
It's here.
It's a Yokai!
-What?
A Yokai's really
appeared in there?
-Help.
There's a huge Yokai
in the auditorium.
-All right.
I'll be right there!
-Master, are you OK?
-Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
I'm fine.
-Master Rikuo, please get back.
-Kubinashi, what's
happening to him?
-I don't believe it.
He's become huge.
-His head has re-attached.
-What the hell?
What is he?
KIYOTSUGU: Shima, what's
going on out there?
The door won't open, Shima.
You there?
-The door's blocked by
some concrete rubble.
I'll be right there.
KIYOTSUGU: What's wrong, Shima?
Shima!
[growling]
-This is bad.
-Protect Master Rikuo.
-Right.
-Leave it to us.
-I'll protect you.
-The weak must die.
That is the code of
the Shikoku Yokai.
-Master, please.
You've gotta get out of here..
-Let us handle this guy.
-Huh?
[scream]
KIYOTSUGU: Shima, what happened?
[growling]
-No one will save you now.
-Master, run away.
-Now, time for you to die.
-No!
[laughter]
-I've killed Rikuo Nura!
Huh?
What is this?
-The darkness signals
the curtain to fall.
Time to get you off
this stage, dog breath.
-Master is OK.
He's alive.
Oh.
Thank goodness.
-Are you Rikuo Nura?
-You've been putting
on quite a show,
getting real carried
away with yourself.
-I don't care who
the hell you are.
I'll kill you!
-I think you've got the wrong
idea that having a big body
makes you strong.
-Don't mess with me.
How can someone like
you have so much power.
I can't accept that.
I refuse to accept it!
-Shima, are you all right?
Hey, Shima.
-Kiyotsugu, there's a
Yokai in the auditorium.
-Leave it to me with my Seven
Branch Sword of Exorcism!
As the proud captain of the
Kiyojuji Paranormal Patrol,
I shall go forth and
exterminate the Yokai!
Haa!
Huh?
Where's my Yokai!?
-Are we safe?
-No.
Let's get out of here right now.
-Right.
-Wait.
That's--
-Why don't you quit
running around already?
-Shut up!
-Hey.
Not bad.
-You're nothing but
a low level Yokai.
Die!
-I'm really getting
tired of hearing
you whine about who's better.
-Huh?
-So I have some news for you.
You're not the only
one who's in imperfect!
-What?
-Damn it.
I won't lose to you.
-Are you all right, Inugami?
-Tamazuki, I haven't
lost this fight yet.
-You're a valuable
comrade, Inugami.
I have no plans of
letting you die just yet.
-Enough with this charade.
-Is that really you, Rikuo Nura?
I wasn't expecting such an
impressive transformation.
Well, well.
It appears I underestimated
you and your abilities.
-What are you really
after, Tamazuki?
-Didn't I tell you already?
I intend to steal
away your fear,
and use it to stand
above all Yokai.
-Funny.
I was thinking the same
thing, little tanuki.
-Well then, I think the time
has come to call it a night.
However, I promise the
next time you and I meet,
I'll take your life.
-Inugamigyoubu Tanuki
Tamazuki, he certainly
likes to make
things melodramatic.
NARRATOR: The evil dog has
lost its vicious fangs.
The decisive battle with
Tamazuki looms on the horizon.
[theme music]
-Hey, Mizumaro,
buy this book too.
MIZUMARO (VOICEOVER):
What is it?
My beloved Nura Clan?
-Lord Gyuki published
it at his own expense.
-It isn't selling. is it?
-I bet it's not.
-Next time-- The 7:3
Pledge of Loyalty.