Umino's love is pure, and
should be savored like a hint of
lemon on fried shrimp...
...covered with shredded cabbage
and sautéed to perfection!
I will never forgive you for
taking away such a deliciously
pure boy's heart!
I am Sailor Moon! In the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
Professor.
Have you found
a new target?
Yes.
There's a chance that the
talisman may be in the pure
heart of a lover.
Is your latest Daimon egg ready
to go forth, Professor?
I'm concerned about the Daimon
eggs you've already wasted!
You've brought me nothing,
not even one talisman!
And then those meddlers, who
call themselves Sailor
Guardians...
...keep finding ways to
destroy each Daimon egg that I
have sent forth!
With the way things
have been going...
...I don't see what can be
gained by releasing more eggs
and sending them out
there on their own.
This time out, I will personally
accompany your egg.
Very well.
[Laughing]
I won't disappoint you.
"Let Moon Help With
Your Love Problems."
Umino?
I guess he isn't here yet.
Usagi.
Huh?
What are you
doing back here?
I need to talk to
you in private.
About what?
Well, Naru has been
acting kinda strange lately.
How so?
It's hard to explain exactly.
Oh, it's nothing,
never min.
It's as though...
Umino, you should
go on home now.
...she's hiding
something from me.
What? I'm not hiding anything
from you. Don't be ridiculous.
It's gotta be something she just
doesn't want me to find out!
[Crying] She probably found a
new boyfriend and doesn't know
how to tell me!
Well I bet he doesn't cook her
favorite fried shrimp with just
a hint of lemon!
[Crying] That's the dish I make
especially for Naru!
Fried with love, sweat, and
tears from my soul!
Sounded great until you got to
the sweat and tears part!
Hmph.
Relax! If it's really bothering
you, I'll see if I can get Naru
to tell me what's going on.
[Gulps]
I'll be forever in your debt,
Usagi.
...broke! And the cat fell
in the peanut butter jar!
So listen, Naru.
Hmm?
I was wondering how
you and Umino are?
Actually, he's been
acting strange.
Huh?
He's been getting nervous around
me all the time now.
Like he has a secret that he's
trying to hide from me.
Seems to be a lot of
that going around.
Huh?
Nothing! So what
kind of secret?
That he's met another girl and
he's not into me anymore.
[Laughing] Oh, please! There's
no way he would cheat on you!
You really think that's true?
Absolutely! Guys like Umino
are lucky to get one girl!
[Grunts]
Obviously you're just too
immature to see what a great guy
he really is!
I'm sorry.
Just forget it.
I'm going home.
Naru!
Well, they're obviously
still into each other.
Ha! The solution is simple! The
way to solve their problem is to
make them realize
they don't have one!
And I know just the person
who can help me!
[Lip Smack] Love problems?
That's my specialty!
I'm gonna talk to Rei!
...So that's the whole story.
You're right. They both appear
to share the same doubts and
feelings.
They need solid confirmation of
their love. Something they can
see with their own eyes.
Wow! You really do know
everything about love!
I even know the perfect
event that'll help them!
Ta‐da!
"Lovers Park?" That
! must be new.
It is. And to kick off their
grand opening, they're holding
an affection contest.
So why don't we enter
Umino and Naru?
[Giggling] Yeah, let's do it!
And if they win, they get to
turn on the love‐light in the
special heart‐shaped monument.
I love it! Mamo and
I should sign up, too!
[Sighs] We're not
doing this for you.
Look, entering them in this
contest will hopefully deepen
their love.
Then the same would be
true for me and Mamo!
But if you win, that defeats the
purpose of what we're trying to
do here. Don't you see that?
Oh, yeah! [Laughing]
You're very smart, Rei!
[Grunting] Why don't you get
going? Those contestant slots
won't last forever!
Mhm!
[Heavy Breathing]
Hurry up! Let's go!
Where are you taking
us, Usagi?
Oh, you'll see
soon enough!
All you have to do is
just trust me! C'mon!
Here we are!
[Screams]
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
Usagi!
What's going on?
I was going to enter you two in
this contest so you could stop
doubting each other
all the time. [Sighs]
[Both] Hmm.
[Both] Usagi, the truth is...
Huh?
[Both] See?
[Both] Hmm?
Umino?
Naru?
[Sighs] The truth is I wanted to
enter the Affection Contest
together with Naru.
Why didn't you ask her? It could
have saved me all this trouble!
Well I just couldn't muster up
the courage to get the words out
of my mouth.
So that's why you were acting so
nervous around me. Wow! You're
pretty silly!
Look who's talking! I heard you
were acting the same way, Naru.
Well he started it.
[Mumbling]
[Gargling]
[Sighs] One! Two!
Three! Four! Five! Six!
Hmm! [Inhales]
Hmph! [Groans]
Now I'm all set for
tomorrow's contest!
I should probably get to bed
early. Beauty rest.
Need to relax! Fall asleep
quickly, okay.
One sheep, baa! Two
sheep baa, baa!
Three sheep, baa, baa, baa! Four
sheep, baa, baa, baa, baa!
Thirty thousand and three sheep,
baa. baa, baa, baa, baa, baa,
baa, baa!
Oh, come on! Why can't I
fall asleep!? Baa, baa, baa,
baa!
I'm sensing an evil presence
coming from somewhere inside
this park.
Then we should expect another
! Daimon to appear very soon.
We mustn't let them get their
hands on any of the talismans.
Good luck you guys!
Thank's, Mommy!
Umino, are you all right?
It doesn't look like
he's all right to me.
[Screams]
Huh? What are you girls
doing here?
Hey! We were looking for you!
Why would you come
to the competition?
We came to cheer on
Naru and Umino.
After all, we are
the Guardians of love!
Plus we thought it
would be fun to watch.
This will be a good
opportunity for me to
learn about relationships.
[All] For what?
For whatever. I don't
know. It's purely research.
Hey, look over there. It's
Haruka and Michiru.
Oh, wow!
Do you think they
! entered the contest, too?
As a couple?
Well I have to say, they sure
! look perfect together!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Please start gathering around
the stage area. The Affection
Contest will begin shortly.
Yay! Let's go cheer them on!
Right!
Hello, everybody! Are you living
a life of love?
The couples gathered together on
our stage today are overflowing
with love and affection.
As you know, they're here to
compete, and by doing so, will
show us whose love
is the deepest.
The winning couple will be the
one who demonstrates that they
truly have the most loving
and purest hearts of all!
[Chuckles]
Hey, good luck Naru!
Go knock 'em out, Umino!
Michiru, you
look beautiful!
Haruka, you look great, too!
Hold on!
Wait, are you here to
cheer on our friends, or not?
'Cause it sounds an awful lot
like you're rooting for the
competition.
[Giggles]
Sorry!
Our first game is just a
warm‐up...
...where the contestants
standing behind me have to guess
which hand belongs
to their girlfriend.
When you've found it,
let me know!
[Crowd Sighs]
Wow, that was really fast!
She went straight
to that hand!
If that's Michiru's hand it
seems to me they're serious
about each other.
Huh?
Okay, now! Shout out your
girlfriend's name!
Why?
[Gasps] Oh come on, now. You
just have to say her name
loudly, so our
audience can hear it.
You're joking right? Why would I
do something lame like that?
Look, I just got this job.
Please, just say her name for
me!
Michiru.
[Chuckles]
[Sighs] Wow!
Okay! Now the rest of you find
your girlfriend's hands!
Alright!
Umino is up next!
Which is Naru's hand?
Here, use my handkerchief.
I don't mind!
I recognize her hand! I'd know
it anywhere!
This one!
Yeah! Now call out your
girlfriend's name!
I'm holding the hand of my sweet
angel, Naru!
Ew, no way!
Sorry, pal! Wrong hand!
He's in big trouble!
I remember the bandage on her
finger! This has got to be her!
Let go of my arm, buster!
Umino, you dummy! That cut was
from months ago!
But I guess he never forgets
anything about me!
Are you all
right, young man?
Yeah, this is nothing compared
to the pain Naru must be feeling
in her heart right now!
[Grunts] Forgive me,
Naru! I messed up!
Time to move on, who's next?
[Sighs] He sure gets worked up
over a silly contest.
I think it's kinda sweet.
Huh?
That he can be so vulnerable and
not afraid for all the world to
see how serious his love is.
For him, it's more
than just a silly contest.
The three‐legged race of love!
Ready, start!
[Cheering]
[Grunting]
Karaoke of love!
[Singing] Oh my love,
is like a tree!
Just stop, Umino.
He's a disaster.
Maybe. But he has
the purest heart.
He's clearly trying as hard as
he can to show his love.
Okay, I'll give him that.
I hope he wins this contest.
And now comes the Grand finale!
Even those who haven't won
previously! Here's your chance
to turn your luck around!
We call it the "Confessions of
! Love Game!" Your scores will be
determined by the audience.
The louder the cheers and
! applause, the higher the score.
So tell me, is everybody
out there ready to cheer?
[All] Yeah!
So let's start with
our leading scorers!
Now what we all want to hear,
tell her how much you love her!
I don't think so.
Show's over.
[Gasps]
We're not participating in the
final game. We're withdrawing.
But why are you withdrawing now?
We only entered your affection
contest to have some fun.
But victory should go to someone
who needs their partner to know
just how pure their love truly
is. We've already got that down.
Cherish your love!
Love must rule everything!
Aww!
That's what we think.
[Cheering]
Bye, now.
[Grunting] It's time to move
to our next couple!
Hey, Hanako, want to
be my woman?
Yes, Takao.
I'm so happy!
I think it's time you get
a new pair of glasses.
Hmm?
[Laughing]
Yo! Love is...
...a battle!
[Screaming]
Hiya!
Sometimes you win,
sometimes you lose.
What a knockout!
And now, my friends, we've come
to our final couple in today's
competition!
You're up!
[Cheering]
All right!
You can do it, Umino!
This is for Naru!
Hmm!
Hmm?
[Screams]
Umino!
He's definitely not off
to a good start.
Poor Umino.
[Sighs] Naru...
You're always so cheerful and
graceful, and your smile is
warmer and brighter
than the sun.
Umino!
I'm so constantly awkward that
at times I'm afraid I might
not be the right person for you.
Sometimes I wonder why
you don't dump me.
I don't know why you stay with
me. Seems like the universe is
just pulling a prank
on the both of us.
I get so scared and
full of doubts, but...
...just seeing your face
makes me so happy.
Know that in order
to protect you...
...my lovely and sweetest
angel...
...I...
...Gurio Umino...
...would die for you.
Oh, Umino.
[Crying] That was so beautiful!
So, hey! What do you think about
this couple!?
[Cheering]
The crowd is going wild! It's
unanimous! You're our winners!
[Cheering]
All right! Now time
to light up your love!
We did it! Right?
Yeah!
And now, I'll light this
sculpture in honor of our love!
This is for Naru and me...
[Gasps]
What the?
[Screams]
Die‐Heart!
[Gasps]
We should run!
But our monument of love
isn't lit yet!
Never mind that!
In the pure heart of the one who
protects his beloved, there must
be a talisman!
[Grunting]
I won't let you hurt her!
Naru, run!
[Screams] Umino!
[Screams]
No!
Umino!
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
Mercury Star Power! Make Up!
Mars Star Power! Make Up!
Jupiter Star Power! Make Up!
Venus Star Power! Make Up!
[Grunting]
[Giggles] Oh, found it!
Not so fast!
Huh? Who said that?
How dare you ruin the light
of love he worked so hard to
win!
Umino!
Maybe Cupid, the god of love,
will forgive you. But I
certainly won't!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Jupiter!
And now, in the name of the
Moon, we'll punish you!
[Chuckling]
Who are you?
I'm here to make sure that you
little girls behave like little
girls.
[Chuckles]
All right! Bring on
the dancing boys!
May I have this dance?
[All] May I have this dance?
Uh, maybe one little spin!
Are you ready
to dance with me?
Yes.
So, you come here often?
[Screams]
[Chuckles]
Hmph!
[Screams]
Huh?
Answering the call from a new
era, Sailor Uranus here to fight
with brilliance!
Also answering the call from a
new era, Sailor Neptune here to
fight with elegance!
Die‐Heart, find dance partners
for these two girls, as well.
Die‐Heart.
Don't bother. It's your
turn to dance!
World Shaking!
Die‐Heart!
[Gasps]
Time to stop fooling
around with illusions.
Right!
[Chuckles]
It's no big deal that you
defeated us again. We'll keep
producing more Daimon eggs
until we wear you down.
Not if we take
you down first!
Let's settle this once
and for all, right now!
[Chuckles] No!
[Grunts]
But I appreciate
the offer, ladies.
See ya!
Damn!
Umino, please don't die!
Let's get that crystal!
Die‐Heart!
Wrong again. There's
no talisman here.
Huh?
Take good care
of him now.
[Grunts]
Oh, you're okay!
Naru?
Die‐Heart!
I'm not gonna let you
pull that on me again!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
Huh? [Screams]
Lovely!
All right! Turn on
the love light!
Let's cheer on the
happy couple!
[Cheering]
Glad it worked.
Yeah, it was a great
idea, Rei!
He looks, so happy!
Well, he definitely
earned it!
So sweet, I wish...
Huh?
My "awkward guy" really
came through.
Yeah. I did.
So, do you know what you're
making me for lunch tomorrow?
Something different. I want to
try deep fried lobster.
Can you afford that?
No.
Yep. Thought
so. [Laughing]
Wow, Haruka is so cool
! and handsome!
Uh, Mako, before you go crazy,
let me remind you once again,
Haruka's a girl!
And that smile,
! it's to die for.
Yeah, but like
I was saying...
She's everything I
! could hope for!
Ah, just forget it.
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
!"Coldhearted Uranus: Makoto in
Danger."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.