Love can come in many
different shapes and forms.
Some people openly
express their feelings,
while some choose to
quietly watch over their
love, wishing only for
their happiness. But a
Daimon targeting the
pure‐ hearted for their
own evil plans? That's
definitely not love!
In the name of the
moon, I'll punish you!
Ohn‐Boda‐Rosha‐Nii‐ Sowakah.
Ohn‐Bazarah‐
Datoban. Ohn‐Arata‐No‐
Sanban‐Bah‐Taraku.
Ohn‐Rokei‐Jin‐Barah‐Aran‐
Ja‐Kiri. Ohn‐Abokya‐Shi‐
Tei‐Sowatah‐Yah‐Untara‐
Tah‐Kanman.
Ohn‐Soba‐Nii‐Soba,
Uhn‐Bazarah, Uhn‐Hatta.
Ohn‐Syu‐Chi‐
Rii‐Sowakah.
I keep having that same
ominous dream over and
over.
What does it mean?
What is this dream
trying to tell me?
"A Man's Kindness:
Yuichiro Heartbroken
by Rei"
Yuichiro!
Huh?
[screaming]
Calm down, it's just me.
What was it
you were peeking at,
so late at night?
[chuckling]It's not what
you're thinking! I'm
actually very concerned
about Rei's health.
Yes, she's been staying
up late every night,
absorbed in her ritual.
But she's not gonna
stop just because
we tell her to. Why
not let it go?
But how can
I do that?!
Huh?
It is not for us to
ask what answer she's
looking for.
There's only one truth.
We have to let her continue
until she finds it.
Her destiny is her own.
I understand
that, and that's why
I can let it go.
Yeah, but...
Uhh...
Ohn‐Lan‐Ken‐Sowakah
Ohn‐Kubi‐Lah‐Ya‐
Sowakah. Ohn‐Kiri‐
Kiri‐Bah‐Sahra‐‐
Hey Rei! Thought you
might be hungry, so I
brought over a pack
of instant noodles.
Ohn‐Rokya‐Roh‐‐ Agh! This is so
frustrating, but
I'm not giving up!
I have all your favorites!"Hi
Curry", ready in three
minutes! How 'bout quick
microwave spaghetti
in meat sauce?!
And let's not
forget an omelette,
plus a fresh‐wrapped
tuna sandwich!
Here's a wonderful late‐
night treat! Grilled rice
balls and a natto roll!
And how 'bout this for a great
dessert? Nata de
coco and bananas!
Noh‐Maku‐Shichi‐Liya,
Chibi‐Yanan‐Tata‐Gya‐
Tah‐Nun‐‐
Oh, Rei. What are you
working on so hard to
divine? Do you know
I'm even in the room?
I'm right here, if
there's anything I
can do to help you.
Rin! Pyo! To! Sha!
Kai! Jin! Retsu!
Zai! Zen!
[gasp]
Ah!
Yuichiro! What are
you doing here?
I was just... I wanted to...
Sorry, but whatever it is, can
it wait? I'm in the middle of
a very important divination.
Okay?
Uh...Alright.
But... You should
tie your hair with
this. You don't want
it to get singed.
Thanks.
Ohn‐Kiri‐Kiri‐Bah‐
Sahra‐Bah‐Sah‐Ri
It's no use. She just
won't stop. I can't
do a thing.
How glorious! I
have to say, this
object is science's
ultimate creation.
Yes. It's a piece
of living art.
Exactly! A perfect description!
I poured my
blood and soul into
creating this masterpiece!
But! The problem is,
no matter how many of
these eggs I entrust to
you, you waste them...
And then allow them
to be destroyed!
I understand, but do
not worry, Professor.
My plans, each perfectly
calculated and
harmonious, are
also works of art.
It's just that I've had
unexpected interference
lately.
I am committed to our
cause and I will find the
talismans needed to
summon up the holy grail.
Yes! You must!
Everything depends on it!
The end of the world!
The coming of darkness
and total destruction!
Can't you feel it?
The deadline is near!
[evil laughter]
Go, Kaolinite.
Complete you
mission.
Sir.
[yawning]
These all‐nighters
really take their toll.
Maybe I'll just skip
the study session.
Poor Rei, she
looks exhausted.
And having said that,
Yuichiro stood there and
looked on as Rei walked
away, down the street.
The end.
Usagi...
Look, I get it. You want
to watch over the one
you love.
Yep! I certainly
know that feeling!
You know, you're quite
the handsome devil!
The pride of Japan!
I'm not all that.
Ah! You've got it all wrong.
I'm just
worried about Rei like
any friend would be.
Worried?!
Yes. She's been giving
up sleep so she can stay
awake, chanting into the
early‐morning hours.
She claims she can
concentrate better
at night.
I'm just afraid she's
going to ruin her
health.
Hey! That seems like
a real obsession...
Something that even
a doctor couldn't
fix.
Does that mean you
know what's going
on with her?
Of course I do! It's obvious!
Poor
Rei! Can't sleep at night?
Oh, please!
Come on! She's lovesick!
What else could it be?
Agh! L‐ Love?!
[growling]
So she's in love,
eh? Who's the guy?!
How dense can you be?!
It's as clear as the
nose on your face!
She's trying to divine
whether the two
of you would make a
good married couple!
Egh... You mean she
might be thinking
about marrying me?
[nervous groans]Oh how
cute, you're blushing!
I get the same feeling
when I fantasize about
marrying Mamo! Wait,
now I'm blushing!
[screaming]
Now don't tell Rei
what I just said,
okay? Bye‐bye!
Rei loves me?!
Oh, gosh!
[screaming laughter]
I'm king of the world!
[chuckle]So this
is what they call
a streetcar.By using it, I can
automatically scan
the people who
get on and off this
public‐transit
vehicle. How very
convenient for me.
Time to go.
That was simple. Now all
I have to do is wait
until someone with a
pure heart gets on.
[giggling]
[groaning]
Come on, Haruka. I have
been staying up late,
but I only yawned once.
[groaning]Still, you have bags
under your eyes.
Hm? I do?
He's touching
her face!
Here. I think I better
give you a lift on my
bike. You're so groggy
you might walk
right into traffic.
[giggling]
Thank you!
Oh, Rei! I've
lost her!
I can't compete. Not
with a man like that!
I can't watch this.
I gotta go...
Agh!
Ready?
Almost. Just
a minute.
What are you doing back there?
What's the deal with that thing?
Well, you see...
This is like my
good‐luck charm.
[chuckling]Well, you don't
have to worry. I'm a
good driver, but even so,
you should hold on tight.
Woo hoo!
Rei!
Time to get up!
[gasp] You alright?
You look like you
haven't been getting
enough sleep lately.
You don't have to overdo
it, just because we
have a test coming up.
It that's all that was
on my mind, I'd have
nothing to worry about!
Excuse me while I
go wash my face.
We should cut her some slack!
Life
is too short! A
girl's gotta love!
Love who? Wait just a minute.
Do you know something
we don't.
Call it a woman's
intuition.
I'm not sure that's
something we should
really be counting on.
Yeah, your intuition
hasn't served you well
on exams.
Uh... Perhaps your intuition
needs more study time.
Ugh!
You don't look
lovesick to me.
Huh?!
I've seen you look happier, even
when things weren't
going very well.
I have to believe
you're worried about
something else entirely.
And knowing you, I'm
sure it has to do with
our new enemy.
Am I right? Please don't
keep something like
that to yourself. You
should tell us about it.
Thanks for your concern, Mako...
The thing is I'm as much in the
dark as you are. I don't know
what's causing this anxiety.
But it's just a
matter of time...
Stop your worrying! The
Sailor Guardians are
ready for action!
But first, the Guardians
have to pass their exams.
[giggling]
Who is that guy? And
where in the world did
he come from?
Dammit!
Huh?
What a beautiful
melody.
Oh my god,
that's him!
[gasp] I'm worried, Michiru.
Is what we're
trying to do here nothing
but a waste of time?
What's the matter,
Haruka? This isn't
at all like you.
What if it's already too
late, no matter what
we do? Are we doing
more harm than good?
[gasp]
Haruka, we knew the
consequences when we
started.
The Wheel of Fortune
cannot be stopped.
We know that a new
awakening will come
soon, but 'til then
all we can do is keep
searching for those
three talismans.
To do that...
we'll have to sacrifice
everything.
Sorry, I guess I've
just been in my head
too much.
I can't believe what
I'm seeing! The two‐
timer!
[growling]
It's unforgivable!
Sailor Moon Super!
Yuichiro Kumada,
was it?
Can we keep this short,
if you don't mind.
I have a lot of
things to do today.
Well, I'll keep it
short alright! Let's
go!
Do I know you? Have
I done something to
offend you?
You know what you did!
And I'll make you pay!
[roaring]
You've gotta be
kidding me...
[grunting]
That must have hurt.
Are you alright?
I'm not done yet,
this fight's just
started!
What's this about?
[yelling]
You're good!
[grunting]
Yuichiro? And
Haruka, too!
Oh come on, pal, give
it a rest, will ya?
Fight like a man!
[yelling]
Yuichiro!
[gasp]
[yelling]
Haruka!
Yuichiro, what's happening
here? You need to explain
yourself!
I see. So you're
defending him,
are you?
Wha‐‐?Stop. Don't
bother, you don't have
to say anything.You
win today, Haruka.
I know you're just a
no‐good two‐timer,
but you got the better
of me as a man.
Excuse me? You need to stop
making poor Rei suffer.
You should break it off
with your other girl.
That's basically all
I wanted to tell you.
But... Uh...
I wish you nothing
but happiness, Rei.
Shouldn't you be
going after him?
Don't be ridiculous.
I really don't care
what he does.
Yuichiro, you idiot...
The rain finally stopped.
Rei's still out there.
I hope she doesn't
come home soaking wet.
I notice Yuichiro's
not around, either.
Maybe the two of them
are off getting cozy!
You know what I mean?
Usagi...
[gasp]
We have a problem!
Come, quickly!
Tell me, why have you
suddenly decide to leave
this place?
I'd rather not say,
if you don't mind.
Hmm...
Well, you have a long
and eventful life ahead
of you. I wish you luck.
I will never forget the
debt I owe you, master.
Wait!
What happened,
Yuichiro?
Where are you
planning to go?
I would prefer to
keep that to myself.
[sigh]
Coward...
You never even
faced me!
[gasps]
You have to go
after him, Rei!
Forget about it.
Come on, Rei!
Yuichiro would come
back in a split‐second
if you'd ask him to.
The stupid jerk wouldn't
even hear me out!
I don't care if he
jumps off a cliff.
[upset sigh]
How can you say that!
Yuichiro was just trying to
do what was best for you.
It's so obvious that
he cares about you
with all his heart!
Oh really?
Then why did he run
away from me?!
Why didn't he even have
the courage to ask how
I felt about him?!
I don't know. But
that's a conversation
you should be having
with Yuichiro.
Usagi...
Get out of here!
Go see him!
You can still make
things right!
Go quickly, Rei!
You can do it!
Good luck!
Thanks, girls!
[gasp]
[scared gasp]
Toden!
[scream]
All passengers, please
board quickly at this
time!
Monster!
We finally caught one.
[scared breath]
Toden! Time to retrieve
this man's pure, loving
heart!
Alright!
Ready!
[gasp]
[painful grunt]
Yuichiro!
Mars Star Power
Make Up!
[yelling]
[laughing]
Hm?!
Stop it! How dare you show up and
attempt to take that man's
pure heart!
I'm Sailor Mars! The
Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and passion!
Not only can I not forgive
you, but in the name of
Mars, I'll chastise you!
[groaning]
Yuichiro!
[giggling]
Toden!
[screaming]
All standing passengers,
please hang onto the
train handles!
This isn't a talisman,
either! Another waste
of time!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[gasp]
I got it!
You people again!
Japan's trains are known
for their safety!
How dare you ruin
their track record?!
So now, in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
Toden, I'll leave
the rest to you!
Tracks! Extend!
What do we do?!
Don't move! All passengers, we
will be departing
shortly!
Forward, check!
Side, check!
Cleared for departure!
[screaming]
Sparkling Wide
Pressure!
Safety First!
Look out!
Toden! Tracks, extend!
[screaming]
Your next stop will
be your last!
Got you now!
Evil spirit!
Be exorcised!
Emergency stop?!
Move! Move!
Now it's my turn!
Here's what happens
when you try to steal
a good man's heart!
Burning!
Mandala!
[groaning]
Warning! No smoking
on the train car!
Alright! Now,
Sailor Moon!
You got it!
Moon Spiral
Heart Attack!
[screaming]
Lovely!
Hmm...
They did a pretty
good job.
[gasp]
Take it easy, Yuichro,
you're injured.
What happened to the monster?
What on Earth are you
talking about? You must have
hit your head really heard.
Wait, isn't that my‐‐?
How about you hold onto
it and take me out to
coffee instead.
I'd like that.
We should go home.
Can you walk?
I think so. You can
apologize to Haruka later.
You tried to fight a
very fragile young lady.
She's a woman?!
Don't be a blockhead, of
course she is. I'll carry
this for you.
Thanks.
Come on now. Lean
on my shoulder.
Nah, I'll be fine.
Stop arguing.
Just do it.
The next episode is a must‐
see for all you true Minako
fans around the world! I'm
taking over the show!
Who died and made you star?! I
excel at sports, I've got a
great figure, and I'm better
than you at studies, Usagi!
Oh yeah?! But I do
have a problem.
I'm missing something
in my life.
Is it a Man?
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: " I Want to Quit
Being a Sailor Guardian:
Minako's Dilemma."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.