Haruka is a very cool person!
Wait,
why is Mako looking
at her like that?
She knows she's a girl, right?
Hey, snap out
of it! Oh no! And now
to make things worse,
Mako gets attacked by the enemy!
Return that
girl's pure heart now!
I am Sailor Moon!
And in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Cold‐Hearted Uranus:
Makoto in Danger!
Oh, did you hear
that? I'm so hungry!
How will I get through
tonight's study session?
[chuckle]I'm afraid you'll
just have to suck it up. But
don't worry, I'm making
some roast‐beef sandwiches
for tonight's get‐together.You
are?! You're the
best! I think the rest of
us totally lucked out,
having a friend who's
such a naturally gifted
cook!
I just love
you, Mako!
[giggling]My cooking isn't
really a natural
talent, or anything.
What?The truth is... I always
felt insecure about the
girlish side of me, so I
took up cooking as
a way to build my
confidence.
That's why I work
so hard to be good
at it.
Ohh...But even if you
couldn't cook, Mako, you'd
still have a million
things going for you!
[chuckle]
Thanks, Usagi.
I'm not kidding. I
completely mean it.
Really? Of course! When we first
met, I thought "Wow, she's
one of the prettiest girls
I've ever seen in
my whole life! Okay,
now you're going way overboard!
But if you keep going I'll make
you a double‐decker sandwich!
Yeah! Alright!
[gasp]
Usagi!
[screaming]
I'm sorry! Are
you okay?!
[grunting]
Are you injured?! Can
you move? Do you feel
any pain?
Ow!
Oh! Haruka!
Bun‐head! Are
you alright?
Don't worry! I'm
totally fine! How
bout you, Mako? Huh?
We need to look at
that! I can see
you're bleeding!
Huh?!
Uh.. Oh.
You're right.
I feel terrible.
It's okay, really.
It's just a scratch.
There's no excuse
for what I did...
I had something important on my
mind and I wasn't
paying attention.
Well...
It's alright.
You never even hesitated
to protect your friend.
Ehhh...
Sorry I gave you
both such a scare.
It's okay!
See ya!
Bye‐bye!
Mako, thanks again for
looking out for me
back there...
Mako!
Agh! Hey... I see the way
you're looking at her.
Are you starting to get
a crush on Haruka?
Uh... Come on, what are
you talking about? I'm
not interested in her!
...Not in that way!
[laughing] Of course you're not!
You're far too boy
crazy!
We must seek out the
Messiah at all costs.
The three talismans
that are key to finding
the Messiah, are sealed
inside pure hearts.
So our first job is
to identify those
hearts.
Even if we have to
sacrifice the people
who carry them?
I'm afraid casualties
will be unavoidable in
carrying out our mission.
All for the sake
of world peace?
That is the ultimate goal. I'm
afraid we have little time left.
The Silence is
approaching.
We must hurry then
and find the Messiah
before the disaster
overwhelms us.
I can feel a
sea‐change...
Yeah, there's something
going on. I sense
it, too, but there's no...
action.
So, do either of you
know where Haruka
happens to live?
No idea. It's
never come up.
You're talking
about that Haruka?
Mm‐hm!
Why are you so interested
in her address? Uh...
Well... Because I have to
return this scarf to her.
Hm...
Hmph! Target is
confirmed, proceed
as planned.
Hmm...
[gasps]
Ahh! Come back! Oh! There
goes my excuse to see Haruka!
Excuse?
Ehh..
Come back here!
Ohh...
Where could
it have gone?
Not here. Oh!
Found it!
Almost got it.
There we go!
Huh?
[growling]
[screaming]
What the hell?!
Scarf...
Your pure heart!
Give it to me!
Ew! What's that?!
It's a Daimon!
[gasp]
Mako!
First we need to transform!
Right! Right! Right!
Moon Cosmic
Power Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon!
Mercury Star
Power Make Up!
♪ Sailor Mercury!
Scarf!
[screaming]
Shine Aqua Illusion!
[growling]
Talk about ruining a
perfectly good morning!
Get away from that
girl, this minute!
Agh! How did they
catch on so quickly?!
Alright, back away
for now, Scarf.
Scarf!
[laughing]
[gasp] It can fly?!
Scarf!
[laughing]
What the heck
was that?!
That girl is their
target this time.
I wasn't able to tell
if she possessed a
talisman or not.
Before I could see,
those two guardians
got in the way.
Why not tell them everything?
Then we'd
all be able to fight
the Daimon together.
The Silence is
approaching.
We both know, in order
to stop it, people will
have to be sacrificed.
You think those
girls can do that?
So... What's
your plan?
The enemy will come
back for that girl
again. We'd better
keep an eye on her.
Sailor Moon Super!
Hey! Mako,
time to go!
If you're looking
for Kino, she
already left.
Eh?
That's really odd...
Ugh! Now
where'd it go?
Mako!
Why didn't you wait
for me? What are you
doing out here?
Sorry to worry you. I
lost Haruka's scarf
right around here this
morning and I'm
still trying to
find it.
What? Listen to me,
Mako. Like I said
to you yesterday...
Oh, you've got it
all wrong, really.
Are you sure?
Absolutely!
Trust me!
Hey! Nice to
see you again.
You're looking well.
Uhh...
Hey, guys.
If you're not doing
anything right now,
you want to come
along for a ride?
Um... with you?
Well, sure!
Huh? Wait, Mako!
In my opinion, I
really don't think
this is a good idea!
Oh. You think it's wrong
for girls to go out on
a drive together?
Uh... That's not
how I meant it,
you misunderstood.
Then you don't mind?
I can borrow
your friend for a little bit?
Assuming you
wanna come.
Sure! Of course!
But... Mako...
Don't say I
didn't warn ya.
This is Michiru, by
the way. She's my
classmate.
I think you and I
have met before...
At the arcade?
Uh... Yeah... By the
way, please don't take
this wrong, but how old
are the two of you?
We started high
school a few weeks
ago.
Started high school?!
But I thought you had
to be older than that
to legally drive a car!
Oh, is that right? Mm..
Oh yeah, well, I was able
to get a license while
I was living overseas.
Huh...
So she says...
Uh...
Those are cute earrings.
They look good on you.
Uh...
You mean that?
You okay with being
dragged away like
this?
Oh sure! No
problem!
I just wondered...
Was there something
you wanted to talk
to me about, Haruka?
Nothing really. I just
wanted to get to know
you better.
Uh... Uh...
[laughing]
What?! A date?!
Agh! Yeah!
Uh‐huh...
And not to get to
gossipy, but her
date is a woman.
Are you sure
about that?
Oh, my heavens!
Did Mako suddenly
change her
orientation?
That doesn't matter!
But wait, there's more!
Her date is Haruka!
Oh?! Well in that
case, I can't
really blame her!
Handsome or not, I
can't believe Mako
would go chasing
after another woman!
You're missing
the point here!
You're one to judge!
Isn't this yours, Rei?!
[screaming]
Get your grubby hands
off my first edition
Sailor Dudettes!
That doesn't matter!
What matter is we all
have to protect Mako!
One thing I'm absolutely
sure of, the enemy is
after her pure heart!
Uh‐huh...
I'm not far. I'm
at Kaiohzu Park.
Don't move, we'll
head right over.
I'll be fine. If the
enemy comes, I'll take
care of 'em!
I'd like to have
the day to myself.
Mako!
Listen to me!
I think you're
being impulsive!
Yeah! How 'bout falling
for someone who is single!
Uh... None of that
matters right now!
But it'll matter to Mako!
She's gonna be
a third wheel!
It's okay! Really guys,
it's not at all what
you think.
How should I say this?
Haruka has a
really cool
personality, you know?
There's nothing
wrong with finding
that attractive.
[giggle]
[gasp]
Uh...
[scream]
Scarf...
Ahh!
Scarf!
[laughing]
[screaming]
Mako!
[gasp] I have no more time
to waste with you! I am
going to take that pure
heart of yours right now.
[groaning]
Run, Haruka, run!
Let Mako go! Or I'm
coming after you!
No! Both of you get
away from here!
Quickly!
You like throwing
rocks, do you?!
[gasps] [screaming]
Agh! Haruka!
Michiru!
[chuckling] The
troublemakers are no
longer a threat. Scarf!
You're clear
to take that
girl's pure heart.
[chuckling]
[growling]
Scarf!
[screaming]
[giggling]
[groaning]
it's all going
as planned.
I feel bad for her,
but it had to be done.
[screaming]
[growl]
[chuckling]
[scream]
[gasp]
You two again?!
Sorry, but we'll be
taking this girl's
heart crystal and it's talisman.
Curse you! Go, Scar!
Get rid of them now!
Scar!
Hah!
We won't let you
have that crystal!
They were waiting just
so they could get my
pure heart?
Hah!
Did they just stand
by and watch while
Haruka and Michiru were
attacked? Damn them!
That's enough!
Huh?!
Only an evil monster would
grab a pure girl's heart!
We, the Sailor Guardians,
will never forgive you!
So now, in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
Venus Love Me Chain!
Burning Mandala!
Ahh! Scarf!
[gasps]
Scar!
This isn't a
talisman, either.
Sailor Neptune!
Come on! We need to
put that back into
this girl, now!
Here you go. Don't
waste any time.
Quickly, Sailor Moon!
Agh! Right!
Those girls are still
in danger here.
Too bad they're
so pathetic.
[screaming]
Deep Submerge!
[painful groan]
Are you alright?
Yeah. Thanks.
I'll be fine.
You need to
take it easy.
No. I just
can't do that.
Jupiter Star
Power Make Up!
Scar!
[grunting]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[screaming]
Jupiter!
Sailor Moon, now!
Moon Spiral
Heart Attack!
[screaming]
Lovely!
Hold on!
I don't know what you
guys are up to in all
this, but you're always
sneaking around, trying
to take pure hearts
for yourself!
In my opinion, you're
no better than the
Daimons!
So what if we are?
I'm not gonna just let
you walk away! I'm
gonna kick your butts!
[attack yell]
[grunting]
Jupiter!
That was childish. You
could have at least
held back a little.
Uranus!
I'm fine.
She's strong.
It's her scarf!
I wonder how
it got here?
We found Haruka
and Michiru!
[gasp]
Haruka! Haruka!
Haruka! Wake up!
You're finally awake!
Thank goodness!
Oh. It's you, Mako!
Where'd that monster go?
Mako says the Sailor
Guardians showed up and were
able to take care of it.
Hm...
Haruka! You're okay!
[crying]
This is my fault. It
only happened because
you were with me.
[gasp]
You got injured!
That monster hurt
your hand!
Hm? Oh! I didn't
realize...
Wait...
Is that?
I'm so sorry. I've
been meaning to return
it to you for a
couple of days, now.
Haruka is just as wonderful
as I thought she would
be. She's really inspired me.
Some day, I want to be
just like her‐‐ someone
who's warm, wise, and
brave.
So guys, how do you feel
about what Mako said
yesterday?
I gotta say, I
think she's serious.
Who knows? Maybe Haruka
just reminds her of that
guy who broke her heart.
Or maybe she just
likes everybody?
You know, I saw
her first!
Oh Minako, you're
just jealous.
Mako?
[happy chuckle]
♪ Sailor Moon!
What do I want
to become?
What are you talking
about, Ami? Ever since
I've known you, you've
always dreamed about
becoming a doctor!
But my dreams don't
get me all charged
up and excited, like
yours do, Usagi.
[giggling] That's because I'm
happy‐ go‐lucky! Believe
me, you're wonderful just
the way you are, Ami!
Usagi...
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'The Labyrinth of
Water: Ami Targeted!'
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.