Kaolinite thinks I have a
And now she even knows that I'm
When Tuxedo Mask tried to
Without my brooch, I can't
"The Stolen Pure
Heart: Usagi's Crisis."
Let Tuxedo Mask go, please!
[Laughing]
Hold it right there!
The Sailor Guardians are here!
You deal with us now!
I'll get
to you later.
[Gasps]
Usagi Tsukino. If you and the
Sailor Guardians want to save
Sorry to say that's where you'll
take your last breath.
[Laughing]
Oh Mamo, no!
Usagi!
Huh?
Who are they?
Lo
oked like Neptune
and Uranus!
They were probably waiting
They're like a
pair of vultures!
Usagi!
Wait!
I know without a doubt, the
Since you can't transform, we
I can't wait.
It's my fault Mamo got captured
I distracted him.
I don't care if it's a trap.
I have to go save him right now!
Usagi!
[Grunts]
[Heavy Breathing]
Haruka!
Funny meeting you, Bun‐Head.
Can you give me a ride,
please? It's important!
Of course.
Usagi! Come back!
Oh no, we're too late.
That idiot always goes off on
her own without thinking.
Do you seriously believe you can
handle this by yourself?!
Usagi.
Huh?
Tell me, did you and your
boyfriend make up?
Yeah. [Sighs]
Hmm.
You look worried, Bun‐Head.
Huh?
People are always sacrificing
What are you
talking about?
Let's just say for example, if
someone you knew was to put
[Gasps]
That person would probably keep
... even if that meant they had
to give up their life for yours.
It may be your friends or even
your parents who make the
We realize there'll
be casualties!
Stop this! It's wrong!
We can't stop! This is our mission!
You think I want there to be
casualties? But if you knew that
...tell me what would you
do different!
Huh?
[Gasps]
It's just how the
world works, right?
[Gasps]
No it's not! The people doing
the sacrificing might be fine
But what about the people who
are the sacrifice?
How can it be all right to
I can't just sit around and
watch others suffer so I can be
I may not be able to figure it
out by myself...
... but if we all work together,
I'm sure we can find a way
We have to try!
You care a lot. Your
heart must be very pure.
You sure this
is the place?
Yes, thank you
for the ride.
[Grunts]
Still okay with
this, Haruka?
Very soon, she'll die.
It can't be helped. In order to
get the Holy Grail, and save the
[Grunts]
[Sighs]
Welcome, Usagi Tsukino.
Now, get into the elevator!
[Grunting]
Come on!
It doesn't look like
it's gonna open!
Fine then.
Stand back!
Hold on! The enemy may be
keeping an eye on the front
All right, but it
might take a while!
K, let's go!
Venus, wait!
Remember, for this plan to work
everything depends on you!
[Gasps]
I'm here, let
him go!
In time. But if you come
any closer, I'll smash your
I beg you not to hurt Tuxedo
Mask. I don't care what happens
Very well.
Cenicienta!
Ready!
[Laughing]
[Screaming]
[Screams]
What was that?!
You two again!
Well, Uranus?
This is...This shines so
What? What are you talking
about? How can it produce so
Impossible!
This is simply a regular
heart crystal.
The brightness in this
case is just indicating
[Sighs] We went through all this
trouble for nothing.
[Sighs]
You all right?
[Gasps]
You, you saved me?
Glad we could.
Hmph! Even if you don't
have a talisman...
I'm planning on taking your life
[Gasps]
What did she say?!
[Laughing]
She's not Sailor Moon!
Who the hell are you?
[Gasps]
You steal an innocent girls's
pure heart, and as if that
I'm offended by
your stupidity!
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
[Gasps]
How could this be?
You're Sailor Moon?
[Grunts]
Is that Minako?!
Hold on.
Something's not quite right.
Whattaya mean? You've got a
She's the real deal!
Trust us we can totally
vouch for her!
If that's true, then
explain who that girl over there is!
I have no idea. Maybe she's one
of my devoted fans! Or not.
What she means is, that girl is
Yeah, what she said!
Hmph! Then this is just some
silly pendant!
[Grunting]
Is that really what she
thinks I sound like?!
Well, now that this little
farce is over...
We don't see any
reason for us to stay.
I'm not about to let you go!
We barely got to talk, why don't
you stay a little while.
We'll take a rain‐check.
Let's go, Neptune!
Right!
[Chuckles] You won't get away.
Hmph!
Cenicienta! Take care of
Yes, Ma'am!
Hah!
[Laughing]
Very well. If you insist on
settling things here and now...
...we accept your challenge.
When I'm done with you, you
Ah hah!
[Exhales]
[Grunts]
Sailor Kick!
[Screams]
You just broke off my hand!
"We shall replace any damaged
[Sighs] Such a relief. I'm still
under warranty.
But they're gonna have to
Talk about rough, you
tried to impale us!
Moon Moony Love Me Moon Chain!
[Screams]
That's not a Sailor Moon move!
Usagi!
It's time to take charge! Transform!
Mhm!
Moon Cosmic Power Make Up!
Wait a minute! But that means
You bet I am!
In fact, I'm the one
and only real deal!
The Pretty Guardian who is super
cool and always in style!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
[Screams]
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
Dammit! You are
the real deal!
Lovely!
[Grunts]
Tuxedo Mask!
Thank goodness!
Oh Mamo, I'm glad
you're okay.
Usako!
Mamo!
Rats! Cenicienta was defeated!
World Shaking!
Hmph!
[Grunts]
Uranus!
Don't let your guard down,
[Chuckles]
I'm going to get all the Sailor
Guardians to join my party.
[Gasps]
Up there!
Looks like Uranus and Neptune
Huh? Why should we?
They've never helped us. Let
them fend for themselves.
Not true! They just saved my
That proves they're not
bad people!
Glad I thought of it! We should
do what we can to help them!
Before we do, I
have one request.
Hmm?
Could I ask you to never ever
wear that disguise again?
What? Why? Is
something wrong?
Luna even lent me your
[Laughing]
Dammit!
[Chuckles]
Hold it right there!
Huh?
This transmission tower sends
out fun TV shows to every
So in the name of all our
viewers, we'll punish you!
Finally, you're all here!
[Grunts]
Now what? You gonna run away
like you usually do?
You think you're so smart, but
you're forgetting that I still
[Gasps] My other
glass slipper!
That's not all I have.
This glass tube contains a
When I combine
it with this...
...the same power Cenicienta had...
...is now mine!
[Gasps] Look out!
[Grunts]
The Professor will be so pleased
You're in pain! You can't keep
fighting in this condition.
It's nothing. I'm fine, really.
Get to safety! We've
got this covered!
You sure?
Come on, this is no fun. The
time for talking is over!
[Screams]
Hurry! Get out of here!
Yeah, you heard her.
Just go!
There's obviously no talisman
to be found here, so there's
Huh, they're right.
[Grunts]
Let's go Neptune. They're
sacrificing themselves here
Why don't we take them
up on their offer.
[Chuckles] I said I wouldn't let
you go.
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
Looks like you won't be going
Oh we're gonna try!
Watch this!
Burning Mandala!
Supreme Thunder!
[Laughing]
It had no effect!
She put such a powerful shield
Huh?
It's too dangerous to
stay put. Let's scatter!
No, wait! We must
stick together!
Huh?
Do you have a
plan, Sailor Mercury?
The only attack that might have
enough force to break through
That's impossible!
She'll take us out before we
have a chance to power up!
[Laughing] End of the line!
[Grunts]
Tuxedo Mask! What
are you doing?
Sailor Moon, I'll
buy you some time!
But hurry!
Be careful!
Hmm.
Hmph!
[Grunting]
Moon Cosmic Power!
Mars Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
[Grunting]
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
I've got you now!
[Grunts]
Now, everyone!
[All] Sailor Planet!
[All] Attack!
Huh?
[Screams]
Did we get her?
[Gasps]
[Grunts] It sure looks like you
No way!
[Gasps]
The people doing the sacrificin
But what about the people who
are the sacrifice?
[Grunts]
But if we all work together I'm
sure we can find a way to handle
Now die!
[Gasps]
World Shaking!
Huh?
[Screams]
[Gasps]
Impossible! [Gasps]
Professor!
[Gasps]
Is she gone for good?
I think so
.
[Gasps] Where are
Uranus and Neptune?
Looks like they already left.
[Gasps]
Well, Uranus. Looks like you're
gonna have to eat your words.
Hey, you don't
need to rub it in.
I just thought, Sailor Moon kind
Usako, I'm sorry about your
Oh, it's really all right.
I'm just sorry that during
You were so brave trying to
protect me. Besides, just having
[Chuckles]
Wow! Things are getting pretty
steamy around here!
[All Talking At Once]
What is wrong
with these girls?
No one's even
listening to each other!
If you girls want to talk all
Is anybody listening?!
It's me.
Tell me, what happened
to Kaolinite.
I see. Well then, I'd like you
to take her place.
You're the only one I can count on, Eudial.
Yay! Summer! Yukatas!
And festivals!
You can't have a Japanese
But the tough part about being
Sailor Guardian is, we can't ge
Especially since another
But a cute friend has come
back to give us a hand.
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
The moonlight is a messenger of love.