Haruka, Michiru, won't you
please stop going after pure
hearts?
I know we've had
our differences, but we
Sailor Guardians fighting
for the same cause, right?
If we work together, I'm
sure we can find a way to
save the world, even without
the talismans.
I know we can!
It's not fair, you know. You
just go into your own world...
...and leave me behind.
[chuckle]
A dream woke me up
this morning.
Oh?
I've had a strange feeling
ever since. It's unlike
Yeah, I know.
So you picked up on it?
Of course. It's very clear.
Today, witho
ut a doubt, a
talisman will appear.
"The Death of Uranus and
Neptune: The Talisman
Appears."
This new program should
allow me to finally pinpoint
Ow!
Thumb tack? How did it get
in there?
Thank goodness I had a
tetanus shot last year!
Huh?
[screaming]
What is going on here? How
did all these lab snails get
into my locker?
Huh?!
Hey, did you hear? Eudial
failed to get a talisman
again!
Oh dear! Don't tell me she
wasted another of the
She spends so much time
planning everything and then
she fails anyway.
That's so true. That old
broad really should retire
already.
You shouldn't talk about her
like that. It's not very
nice.
I wonder if my turn is
coming up next?
Don't count on it! This is
very hush‐hush. But the
professor called and said he
had something urgent
to tell me.
What?!
That's not fair!
Why would he only call you?
We're all in this together!
Agh! How dare they stand around
making fun of me, hoping to
take over my job!
Did they forget who trained
them in the first place?
Especially Mimete!
She's so two‐faced!
She always plays innocent in
front of me, talking in that
sticky sweet voice. But
the truth is, she's quite
underhanded. I'm pretty sure
she's the one who put the
tack in my slipper, and
those snails in my locker!
Luckily, today is a holiday.
If I find a talisman with my
new computer program
before the break is over.
I'll remain in the
Professor's good graces.
And when that happens I'll
show them who's boss!
Yes!
Now I'm scanning only the
top possibilities.
When the scan is complete, I
should be able to pinpoint
Huh?!
Seriously? They're the ones
who have the talisman?!
Hi, you've reached Haruka
Tenoh. I'm not here right
Hello Miss Haruka Tenoh...
This is Eudial. I hope I'm
not interrupting a private
moment. [laugh] Are you
surprised? Now that I know
You wanna know something
even more surprising? I've
just located someone
who actually holds a
talisman this time! And I'm
Victory is so sweet! I'm
sure you‐‐
Hi, you've reached Haruka
Tenoh. I'm not here right
Hey! The recording time on
your machine is way too
Anyways, just
wanted to share my good
to join me, since
we're both searching
ambush. And I haven't
revealed your secret
identities to my superiors.
If you're interested in
checking it out, come to the
I get the sense she's
telling the truth about
actually finding a talisman.
Yeah. That would explain
what we've been feeling.
Guess it's time.
My hands got dirty long ago.
There's no turning back now...
I'll do whatever needs to be
done to get that talisman!
Michiru?
Hey! What is it?
Haruka...
It'll be all right.
No matter what. I'll always
love your hands.
What is so important about
these talismans?
Our mission is to find and
gather them no matter what!
At the cost of harming the
lives of countless innocent
people?
That's right! We'll do
whatever is necessary.
Are you saying that we have
to become enemies?
Yes. We can never
understand each other.
But why not? We're all
Sailor Guardians aren't we?!
Stop! We must take a
different path to
reach our goals.
We won't have any regrets
sacrificing anyone.
Even though that per
son may have a pure heart.
We have to take it.
Hey, lazy bum, you've
got a call.
It's from some
guy named Haruka.
Huh?!
Wait! What's that? Haruka and
Michiru called Usako to go
and meet with them?
I don't like it. If they
really are Uranus and
Oh, I doubt that.
I still wanna believe
they're not bad people.
Hm? What is it?
Wow! This is amazing!
I never knew there was a
giant aquarium at the top of
this building.
I bet all of our friends
would love this place.
You two all right?
No. This is the last time we
are ever going to see you,
Sailor Moon.
Come on! Don't be like that!
We're all Sailor Guardians.
You guys just have to give
us a chance, that's all!
I won't allow your opinions
of how we should be
[gasp]
I'll hang onto this for now.
Haruka, wait! Stop being so
determined to take pure
hearts away from people!
You stop. And make no
mistake, if you interfere
with us again...
...you'll die.
Uranus Planet Power!
Make Up!
Neptune Planet Power!
We're searching for three
talismans, which have been
sealed away in pure hearts.
If we don't gather all
three, the Holy Grail will
not appear.
The Silence is coming to
this world. All will be
the Holy Grail. She's the
only one who can use its
power to save us.
Holy Grail? Messiah?
That's our
business, not yours.
Haruka! Michiru! Wait!
Do you want to save them?
They're headed into a battle
that was predetermined by
their destiny.
But today, things are
especially dangerous for
them.
Who are you?
I am Setsuna Meioh. I am an
old friend of theirs. I've
known them a long time.
And you say they're in
danger?
Very grave danger. But if
you want to save them it's
going to be very risky for
you, since you can't
transform.
I don't care! Just please
tell me where they are
going! I want to help!
Sailor Moon Super!
Do you see that?
Yeah!
The Marine Cathedral. Looks
like it's still under
construction.
I guess the person with the
talisman should already be
here.
Uranus!
You do understand. We're
going to take the talisman,
If one of us gets into
danger, the other will have
How could I forget that?
[chuckle] Just makin
g sure.
Did she invite us here just
to play hide and seek?
Neptune? What's wrong?
What the hell?
Uranus!
Eudial set us up.
This was a trap!
[chuckle] You fo
ols. Of
course it was.
Now. Game on!
[nasty laughing] Take this,
and that, and this, and
that!
[nasty laugh]
World Shaking!
Deep Submerge!
[chuckle] How's that?
Look out!
[gasp] Neptune!
[nasty laugh] Sailor Uranus!
I've taken the holder of the
Talisman!
What are you saying?!
[chuckle] I was completely
surprised myself.
I have a feeling that even
you two never realized it.
What are you talking about?!
I'm saying that one of the
talismans was sealed inside
[chuckle] I'm going to go
ahead now and extract the
talisman from her! If you
care to watch, go to the
chapel down at the end of
the walkway.
The talisman holder is
Neptune? Impossible!
Neptune?
Neptune!
[nasty chuckle]
You fell for it!
You fool! If anyone
other than me passes
Eudial, how dare you!
In case you're wondering, I
haven't extracted the
talisman from Neptune yet.
I've decided to extract the
other talisman first.
The other one?
There are two here?
I'm pointing right at it.
Like me, you were willing
to kill anyone
to acquire talismans.
When all you had
to do was kill
yourself to get one.
Uranus!
[chuckle] As you say, I'm
like you, so I doubt very
much I'd have a talisman.
They're sealed away
in pure hearts.
We'll see soon enough. Of
course, you won't have much
time to do so, because
once I shoot you with this
gun, you'll die.
[nasty laugh]
Uranus!
[painful screaming]
Haruka... I won't let you die!
Neptune! No! Stay away!
[painful screaming]
Neptune!
Haruka!
Out of ammo.
So this is a talisman...
Get ready... I'm
taking yours next.
The talismans were sealed
inside of us this entire
time?
Help me understand! Is this
the price we must pay for
our actions, Messiah?
Stop right there!
[gasp]
The Messiah?
Why are you here?
[attacking yell]
Michiru, wake up!
Please, talisman! Turn back
into Michiru's pure‐heart
crystal!
Stop!
Huh?
Our job was to fin
d the
talismans. Now we're done.
What?! But Michiru will die!
This isn't fair, Michiru...
Going into your own world
without me.
You can have that back now.
Can't believe you did
something so stupid
without it.
[gasp] Don't!
Let go!
I've got one, too!
There's gotta be a way to
save the world without the
talismans!
How?!
I don't know... But I'll find
a way. I promise.
It's strange. Despite
everything that's happening,
When you showed up back
there, for a moment I
Which is ridiculous, because
there's no way you could be
her...
Haruka?
Sailor Moon, find the
last talisman.
And save this world...
[gasp] No!
Haruka, don't!
Haruka... Michiru...
I've finally obtained two of
the three talismans. The
Don't be so sure, Eudial! I
won't let you keep them.
I'd like to see you try and
take them! Your special
attack doesn't work on me.
Maybe not, but I won't lose.
I'm determined to save
Haruka and Michiru's heart
crystals! I will
never give up!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "The Holy Grail's
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.