You know Chibi‐Usa, if you
were planning to come
back, you could have at least
given us some warning!
We already have enough problems
to deal with as we try
to handle the Daimons and
the mysterious Guardians!
So watch yourself, and don't get
into any trouble as Sailor Chibi
Moon, okay? Or else...
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Hello everyone, it's
me Small Lady.
You also know me as Chibi‐Usa.
I've returned to the 20th
century to complete my training.
I look forward to learning from
each and every one of you.
"Making New Friends: Chibi
Moon's Adventure!"
Alright, alright, so you're
back. Who the heck decided
that would be a good idea?
Oh! I almost forgot. I have a
letter here from Mommy!
A letter?
Let's see it.
Why don't you read it, Minako!
Me? Uh, sure.
Why you little!
The letter says, "Wow, I can't
thank you enough for allowing
Small Lady to train with you."
"Please take good care of my
daughter while she's there.
Signed Neo Queen Serenity."
That's it.
You're kidding.
That's all she said?
When you remember that Neo
Queen Serenity is Usagi, then
the letter makes sense.
Mhm.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I must say, you do
have a point Luna.
It looks like a
child wrote it!
[Screams]
Look at that,
she's right!
See there!
Oh my gosh, her
participle's dangling!
I think part of this
is in Hebrew!
She spelled "daughter"
with a q!
Is that so surprising? Don't
forget we're talking about
Usagi!
Hey guys, we're supposed to
be focusing on Chibi‐Usa
here, right?
[Sighs]
I see she mentions training,
but training in what?
I don't understand. If
it's training to become a
princess, then there's no
reason to send her here.
I sure hope she doesn't pick
up Usagi's clumsiness.
You're right, that
would be a disaster!
Yeah, the Sailor Mars in my
future told me all kinds of
silly stories about Usagi
that I didn't already know.
[Screams] What did you
tell her, huh?!
How should I know?! Go ask the
Mars in the future!
It's still you!
You don't have to worry, I don't
plan on becoming clumsy like
Usagi.
We'll help you in anyway we can,
so don't be shy about asking.
Thank you. Well, I'm
off to train!
[Yelling]
Wait, there's another
note inside.
"P.S. Dear Usagi
of the 20th century..."
"Looking back on my life, I
realize now that I should
have studied much harder while
I was still in school."
"Teehee my bad."
[All] Yep. Definitely Usagi.
But I hate studying!
[Crying]
Wow, it feels so great to be
back in the 20th century!
Small Lady. Your final
training as a princess is to
find and make new friends
back in the 20th century.
Make new friends?
Yes.
A destined encounter
awaits you there, my child.
It will help you
grow as a person.
[Giggling]
Huh, so where
do I begin?
Huh?
[Gasps]
Is this the destined encounter
that Mommy was talking about?
Um, this toy, does it
happen to belong to you?
Yeah, it's mine! What's it to
ya? Ya got a problem with that,
little Miss Pink‐Hair?
So tell me something, and
don'tlie. Do you prefer bell
peppers or pickled scallions?
I can see the two of us doing
the town, hitting all the spots!
If we had midnight coffee
together, we'd be drinking
'café au late!'
Whoa!
What's the matter, babe?
Pull yourself together!
Your wounds are serious,
but I can help!
I will have to use my final
resort, however! Look at this!
[Screams]
This is my true nature.
I am an elephant!
Oh, you stupid boy!
Ouch! Am I being punished in the
name of the moon?
Oh your punishment's
just starting! Wait
'til we get home, mister!
Unhand me you
ugly monster!
Ew, that was so disgusting. I
feel like I should go home and
take a bath.
Hmm?
[Sighs]
Where'd he go? I'm sure he came
through this way.
Hey, Chibi‐Usa!
Huh?
Mamo!
[Screams] It's you!
It's really really you!
Hey guess what, Mamo!
I came back here to train!
Is that right?
Absolutely! Mommy and Daddy from
the future said it was very
important!
Chibi‐Usa! Find somebody else to
annoy, Mamo and I happen to be
on a date right now!
Whatever, he's
my Mamo!
Don't be silly, you're just a
kid! You're ruining my day and
I don't like it!
How about we sit down and eat
this takoyaki together?
Mmm! This is good!
Let me feed you, Mamo.
No way, I'll
do it!
[Screaming]
Well, look at this picture
perfect moment.
Huh?
Hey there, kiddo. I haven't seen
you since, well, the festival.
Haruka! Michiru!
Perfect. Just like
my Mommy and Daddy.
Uh, Chibi‐Usa. I should probably
let you know that Haruka is a
woman.
And, let me remind you, your
Mommy in the future is me.
You know what, I can
believe Mamo is my Daddy,
but I still really have
my doubts about you!
Oh yeah?!
Yeah!
[Sighs]
[Grunts] That's enough from
the both of you!
[Both] Sorry.
I hate to interrupt this famiy
moment, but would you like to
join us for some tea?
Thanks, but...
Yes! That sounds like it would
be great! I was thinking about
a nice hot cup of tea!
And that's not all! I was also
thinking about a cake with cream
filling...!
Uh.
No cream filling?
Oh! I found you!
This is Tamasaburo. The head
tea‐master of the Yaburakoji
Burakoji family.
Hello! Thank you
for coming.
[Grunting]
We were destined to meet.
[Laughing]
Ah yes, tea is wonderful. It
soothes the soul! [Laughing]
Ahh.
[Grunts] Too hot!
Dammit!
[Grunts] That's enough for
today. Wait, that's it!
Excuse me, did you
say "tea ceremony?"
Hmm, I found
him, sir.
Excellent! Now that we have a
target, I will prepare a Daimon
to help you retrieve his pure
heart crystal! [Laughing]
[Laughing]
Chagaama!
[Grunting]
Hey Chibi‐Usa, my legs
are numb. Wanna go home?
I can handle it, you're
such a lightweight.
[Grunting]
[Chuckles] Here, try
some of this.
Wow! Dango!
Thanks!
[Clears Throat]
[Gasps]
[Cries]
[Giggles]
[Silently Screams]
[Panting]
Huh?
[Silently Screaming]
If your legs are getting tired,
feel free to sit however you
want.
Thanks, but really
we're fine.
How about something to take your
mind off the pain?
[Grunting]
Whoa, impressive.
Well, how very
considerate of him.
[All] What?
He's doing that just for your
benefit. The Tea Master is
trying to get you two to relax.
You may not know this, but that
teacup is a national treasure.
They say it's worth millions.
Huh?
Did you say "millions?!"
Yes, but it's okay.
No it's not! You've gotta stop
that! You're gonna break it!
My legs are numb!
[Screams]
[Gasps]
[All] Huh?
You guys are heavy.
Uh, well, at least
these are new socks.
I've had it with you! You
embarrassed me in front of
Tamasaburo!
I'm starting to hate you,
Usagi. You're awful!
Excuse me, I was embarrassed n
front of Haruka and Michiru!
Yeah, but you deserved it.
[Grunts]
What?! Why you!
Usako.
[Sighs]
You like Tamasaburo, is
that right Chibi‐Usa?
Huh?
I guess so.
Before I left, Mommy said...
...I should go and make lots of
new friends in the 20th century.
She also said that a destined
encounter would await me here.
I see. I'm getting the
sense you don't have many
playmates that are close
to your age in the future.
Is that true? Why didn't you
tell us that before? We'd be
happy to help.
Trust me, your helping would
just make it more complicated.
[Grunting]
Hey there, take it
easy Usako. Come on.
Just put aside your differences
and make up, okay?
Huh?
Hmm?
Hmph.
That's it. I'm definitely going
to become his apprentice.
Don't get my kimono dirty.
You don't even wear it anymore,
so what does it matter, Miss
Stingy!
Don't call me stingy!
Stingy, Stingy, Stingypants!
In that case, return
the kimono! Huh?
[Gasps]
That's Eudial!
She's going into
Tamasaburo's house!
[Grunting]
Luna!
Come on, what are
you doing there!?
I'm stuck in this bush and I
can't get through!
Ugh, this is so like you!
Okay, okay, but give me a hand
for now, will ya!? [Grunting]
[Giggling]
Hmm?
Oops, I think I might
have hit something.
Hello, who are you?
Gottcha!
[Grunts]
[Screams] Tamasaburo!
Moon Prism Power! Make Up!
[Grunts]
Hmph!
Well, that was easy.
Hold it!
Huh?
You can back off right now! I
won't let you take Tamasaburo's
heart!
I am the Pretty Guardian
Trainee who fights for love
and for justice!
Daimon! Show yourself!
And in the name of the future
Moon, I'll punish you!
What was that?
I said in the name of the
future Moon, I'll punish you!
Chagaama!
This girl is in our way!
Get rid of her!
Boil and bubble, this
girl is trouble!
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Now, hand over
the pure heart.
World Shaking!
[Gasps]
Deep Submerge!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Answering the call from a new
era, Sailor Uranus here to fight
with brilliance!
Also answering the call from a
new era, Sailor Neptune here to
fight with elegance!
[Coughing]
I see it's
you two again.
Thank you.
Actually, we're not
here to rescue you.
Uh.
Too bad, Eudial, but this heart
isn't a talisman either.
Failed again?!
All right, Chagaama, I'm gonna
grab some coffee and get
a massage, take care of the
rest for me, will you?
Adios!
What a selfish woman.
Oh very well, I'll
get rid of them all!
Huh?
Hey! Where did everybody go?
Huh? You're right!
They're gone!
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
Hmm.
[Slurping]
Ahh that was good.
[Grunting] Hey! Cut that out!
Oh boy. Chibi‐Moon is
fighting her all alone!
Hurry up and transform, Usagi!
Huh, no kidding.
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
Chibi‐Moon! Leave
the rest to me!
Hmm?
And now ladies and gentleman,
boys and girls, the wait's
finally over!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
What took you so long?
Hey! You ran ahead without me!
What was I supposed to do?
Don't blame me!
You're a klutz!
[Grunts]
Allow me to show you both my
hospitality!
Here's some more!
And another!
[Grunting]
Boil and bubble, here you go!
[Screams]
Wait! Wait! Have
some more!
[Gasps]
I'm offering you some
hospitality!
We don't want it!
[Grunting] That's the
rudest thing anyone's
ever said to me!
[Screams]
I'm going to give you this
whether you like it or not!
You are a terrible hostess! A
tea master treats every guest
with the utmost respect.
That's the true essence of the
tea ceremony. Understand?
Thanks for your help,
Tuxedo Mask!
[Chuckles] Very well, it seems
the time has come for me to
demonstrate my true hospitality.
Yes my friends, I think you'll
be surprised by what I have to
offer.
[Gasps] Finish her
Sailor Moon!
Uh, right!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[Laughing]
No, wait, I'm not ready yet!
Please...lovely!
That was darn close.
Too close.
So Sailor Moon,
listen I...
What is it?
I just want to
say, thank you.
I have to say, that little one
put up quite a good fight.
She's so cool.
This time, I'm determined to
become Tamasaburo's apprentice.
Oh, hey look.
There goes Haruka
and Michiru.
Oh yeah. They're sure
leaving in a hurry.
Sorry to keep you guys waiting.
[Screams]
I found a great new approach
to presenting my teas!
It came to me in a dream
about the Sailor Guardians.
I am the Pretty Head Tea‐master,
who teaches tea and etiquette!
I am Sailor Tamasaburo! Yeah!
[Gasping]
[Grunting] Dammit!
Whoa! Easy there, Mako! So
who dumped you this time?
That's not what happened, Usagi.
Take a look over there.
Who are you talking about?
You mean that monk? Hold
on! Does he resemble the
guy who broke your heart?
Oh come on, Usagi,
it's nothing like that!
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"I Want Power: Mako Lost in
Doubt."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.