Chibi‐Usa has a boyfriend?!
As her future mother, I have
to do something to help. I
know! I'll play Cupid, and
make sure the two of them
become a happy couple!
Alright, you two, hit it
off! Hey! You there, the one
who's trying to mess with
their relationship!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Art is an Explosion of Love:
Chibi‐Usa's First Love
How can there be nothing
to eat here? [sigh]
There's never any
food in this house!
Oh! Here we go! Something
in the oven smells great!
[giggle]
Come to mama!
[amazed gasps]
All right, help yourselves,
everyone!
Wait a minute, where did
that apple pie come from?!
You didn't happen to bake
that, did you, Usagi?
No way! I found it in the
oven! The only thing I
can assume is that Mom
must have baked
it for us!
Well that's a relief! So, it
should be safe to eat!
Uhh...
We wouldn't want to get
hospitalized from food
poisoning and miss
the entrance exams!
Hey now! What's that
supposed to mean?
Oh, nothing. Here you
go, everybody!
Wow! How delicious! This
apple pie is so 'apple‐y'!
[nervous chuckle]
Minako, you really
need to work on your adjectives.
But it is apple‐y!
Hey Usagi, do you know what
happened to the apple pie
that was‐?
[screaming]
[gasps]
I can't believe you all
helped yourselves to my
apple pie!
Wait... Are you saying...
...you made this pie?
Yeah, I made it
all on my own!
Usagi, I thought you said
your mom baked it!
We are very sorry.
But have no fear,
Chibi‐Usa!
In the name of Mars, I will
chastise Usagi for you! Agh!
Agh!
Oh, Rei. You traitor!
Ah! This is terrible!
I wanted Masanori
to have that pie!
Huh? Wait a minute,
who's Masanori?
Uhh...
Oh he's... no‐one special. I
got to go! See you guys.
And Usagi! I'm not gonna
forget about this! You
owe me big‐time!
Usagi. Where's
Chibi‐Usa off to?
To the Juban Art Class. I
don't know why, but she
suddenly decided she
wanted to learn
how to do sculpture.
Oh really? Well, maybe
that Masanori is a friend
she met there.
Yeah, a boyfriend. And
judging by this delicious
apple pie, it seems
to be serious.
So you think she went to all
of this trouble, just for
this boy?
Now I feel really guilty.
And we've almost finished
the pie...
Yeah, you're right. Well
there's no sense in leaving
leftovers.
This is Usagi's fault. She
should go apologize.
Sounds good to me!
Huh?! No fair...
It's Masanori! Huh?
[gasp]
She's here!
Who in the world is
he waiting for?
Uh... Michiru?
Oh! Hello, Masanori!
Nice to see you.
Yeah... Me too.
Is something wrong?
I got these flowers for you.
I really hope you like them.
They're such lovely roses!
In the language of flowers,
they mean passionate love...
This can't be!
[screaming]
Well thank you.
It's very sweet.
[growling]
Oh! Well hello
there, Chibi‐Usa!
Uhh...
Come on, you two,
it's time to go in.
Class is about to start. We
don't all want to be late.
Yeah! Right!
Come on! I am not giving
him up that easily.
[nervous giggle]
Darn. This really stinks.
How come I'm the one who
has to check on Chibi‐Usa?
Are you serious, Usagi?
Don't forget, you're the one
who took her apple pie.
So now, take
responsibility.
Fine, fine, fine!
[groan]
Gosh. This really
doesn't look right.
What are you making
there, Usagi? A vase?
Uh, actually, it's
the Holy Grail.
I saw a picture of it
once in Mommy's room.
It was so pretty.
It was decorated with
lots of jewels. Ever
since then I've wanted
something like that
for myself.
Hm. Maybe I can
give you a hand.
I think adding this piece
right here would help it.
That seems to be more
like it, from what I've
heard. If you add beads
for jewels, it will look a
lot like the Holy Grail.
You're right, it will!
You're really good,
Masanori!
Nah, I'm not that good.
So he must be the boy
she was talking about.
You're right. It looks like
they get along really well.
Masanori is so nice and
cute. I like him so much.
He must be my destined
partner. I just know it!
Oh! It looks like Michiru
is taking a class, too.
You're right. Well there
must be a painting workshop
next door.
Hi, Masanori. Don't go
helping Chibi‐Usa too much!
She should really be
doing it on her own.
Okay, sorry.
Good luck, you two. I'm
looking forward to seeing
your finished projects.
Wow! She is so wonderful!
Game on, Michiru! I
haven't lost to you yet,
and I won't!
Ah ha!
So that's how it
is I get it.
I know that look. What
are you plotting?
Isn't it obvious? I'm going
to bring Masanori and
Chibi‐Usa together, so
they can be a couple.
Huh?! Usagi!
[chuckle] Hello, Eudial?
Chin Chin Tei, can I take
your ramen order?!
Are you sure this
isn't Eudial?
No. Chin Chin Tei!
In that case, I'll have the
shoyu marinated butter corn
miso ramen with extra pork.
Hmm...
[phone ringing]
Hello, Eudial speaking.
Hello? Hello?
[chuckle] Hello, Eudial...
Is there something the
matter, Professor?
You paused for a moment
before you answered.
No, no, just hungry. I'm
calling to find out if
you've located the
next target yet.
Yes, I have, and I'm sending
you the data as we speak.
Oh my. What a lovely statue.
I agree, and I bet you'd
never guess it was created
by a ten year old boy. He's
an artistic prodigy named
Masanori Tsuzuki.
His keen aesthetic sense and
pure‐hearted devotion to
creating art, leads me to
believe he may
possess a talisman.
Excellent! And you're right,
a gifted artist may hold
the key to bringing
us the Holy Grail!
There's no time to waste! I
will create an appropriate
Daimon immediately!
Chokokka!
Sailor Moon Super!
I took a look around, but I
didn't observe any activity
by Eudial or her group.
Good. I guess that means
we can both relax this
afternoon.
By the way, where did those
flowers come from?
You're nosey...
Yeah, so?
[laughter] What's so funny?
Are they a
gift from a boyfriend
or something?
Well of course.
Really? Are you telling me
there's a guy out there
who actually has the nerve
to be your boyfriend?
Now that's a surprise. It's
not like you to be jealous,
Haruka.
Hold on there, I'm not
jealous. I just don't want
you going around out there
in the world, looking at
anyone else but me.
Okay! So in other words,
you're completely jealous!
Chibi‐Usa...
[screams]
[giggles]
Have no fear... Your
Cupid has arrived!
[groan]
What are you talking about?!
Hey, Usagi, is this
your older sister?
Well... yeah,
something like that.
Nice to meet you, Masanori!
[giggle] I'm so glad
you've become such good
friends with our Chibi‐Usa!
Oh, sure! I have
to go now.
[giggle] Alright,
Chibi‐Usa!
I got you set up! All you
have do is go in and close
the deal!
[growls] Go home, Usagi!
Unless you want me to
step on you again!
[gasp] What the‐ ?
[screaming]
Everyone remain calm!
There's no need to panic!
Who in the world are you?!
Hm?
Gotcha!
[screaming]
[gasps]
Oh dear...
There go my plans for a nice,
quiet afternoon. Don't sound so
disappointed. Now come on, it's
time we get down
to work, Michiru.
Uranus Planet
Power Make Up!
Neptune Planet
Ah ha! I figure this one
has to be a talisman.
[gasp]
So it's you two again!
Well, I'm not going to let
you interfere! Daimon,
show yourself!
Cho... kokka!
Now's our chance!
No, Chibi‐Usa! Think about it!
If you transform
here, you're gonna
expose your identity!
Then I'll have to fight
without transforming!
[screaming]
How awful! She's barbaric!
You have some nerve, talking
about barbaric! I'm not
letting you take his heart!
Usagi?
What a bad little girl you
are! Really, look at the
mess you've made!
Oh, look who's talking!
You attacked us!
[surprised gasp]
Hey, what are you doing?!
Give back Masanori's heart
crystal, right now!
Don't worry about a
thing, little one. You
can have it back.
Turns out it's not a
talisman, after all.
Well, that's a relief!
Okay! I'm backing out!
Take care of the
rest, Chokokka!
[evil chuckling]
Cho... kokka!
Acho! Acho!
Acho cho cho!
We're at a disadvantage.
Big‐time.
I think you're right.
[gasp]
Oh no, you don't!
Oh brother, this is
terrible! Just look at the
mess they left in here!
Well don't just stand
there! Transform!
Oh yeah, of course!
You'll be okay now.
Stay here until you
feel stronger.
I found... my goddess.
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Moon Cosmic Power
[attack grunt]
Acho!
That was weird... It
was almost too easy.
Greetings, my friend! You're
Art Oh‐Oh‐One... Beyond the
Massacre!
Now go! Show them
art is an assault!
What the‐ ?
Uranus!
Art Number Oh‐Oh‐Two! I'll
call you Silent Ambition!
Can I interrupt? How 'bout
making pieces that are
easier to comprehend?
[laughter] My art
is avant‐garde!
[nasty laughter]
Your evil hands have tainted
the holy spirit of art,
which is unforgivable!
That's right, and on top
of everything else, you
put my precious
Masanori in danger!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for Love and
for Justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
And in the name of the
future Moon, I will also
punish you!
[nervous gasp]
Double Sailor Moon Kick!
Cho!
[screaming]
Hey you! Get off me!
I would, but I can't move!
It's crushing us!
It's dissolving. I see,
so that's how it works.
Uranus! I figured it
out! That creation's
weakness is water!
Got it!
Ah! You destroyed
my creation!
Sure did... And
you're up next!
Your weakness is
water, as well, right?
[scared gasp]
Deep Submerge!
[screaming]
Looks like we're saved.
You're right. So you can get
off of me now!
Looking back, I should
have made sure my clay
was waterproof!
Okay, you two. Time
to finish the job.
Thanks, we've got this!
Just leave it to us, ladies!
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
Huh?
Well hurry up, what
are you waiting for?
Oh! There it goes!
[groaning]
Okay!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[nervous gasps]
Lovely!
We'll meet again,
I'm sure of it.
So long.
Those two are definitely
more reliable than you,
Sailor Moon, and
cooler looking, too.
Did you hear me ask
for your opinion?!
Thanks for the walk, Usagi.
Masanori, it's alright for
you to call me 'Chibi‐Usa'.
Alright, I'd like that. I'll
see you in class then,
Chibi‐Usa.
Oh, I forgot...
Huh?
What is it?
I want you to have this.
I just finished it.
Wow, it's me!
See you soon!
Thank you so much, Masanori!
Way to go, young
lady! Very smooth!
Huh?
Chibi‐Usa! Congratulations!
You guys were watching?
Hey, just this once, I think
you should really be
grateful to me.
It's because of me that
you and Masanori even
became friends in
the first place.
You're kidding, right? All
you ever did was tease me
about my feelings for him!
She definitely has a point.
Shut your mouth, cat!
More importantly, what are
you all going to do about
my apple pie, the one you
stole from the oven?!
What?! You're still
angry about that?
The pie's gone, isn't it?!
Calm down, kiddo. I'll
be happy to bake you
another one.
That won't make up for it!
We hear you loud and clear.
But don't forget, it was
really all Usagi's fault.
That's true.
Come on! Usagi, there's
no way around it.
You have to find a
way to make amends.
It was sitting there I
wasn't trying to steal it!
Well are you ready
for your punishment?
No! Please forgive me! I
promise, I'll never take an
unattended pie again!
[crying]
Hey, come back down here!
Forgive me,
Chibi‐Usa! Please!
Why should I? You did
this! Come down here
and face the music!
Oh wow, can you
believe this?!
Mamo was invited to attend
an international party!
That's Mamoru for you!
Hey, look! He's talking to
that handsome foreign guy
in another language!
That's Mamoru for you!
Wait a minute, how are
we able understand
what they're saying?!
I don't know.
This makes no sense!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'Usagi Dancing
to the Waltz'.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.