Eudial set up a trap to lure
in Uranus and Neptune, so
she could steal their pure
heart crystals. And they
turned out to be the
talismans everyone had been
searching for! Hang in
there, Haruka and Michiru!
I'm on the case, and I'll
find a way to save you!
No matter what, I will
protect this world.
Uranus...
Please don't die... How do
we return the talismans
to your bodies? Just tell
us what you need us to do!
Listen, Bun‐head... I mean...
Sailor Moon. [gasp]
Don't worry about us.
Only the talisman's
matter now...
Whatever else happens,
you have to protect...
...these talismans and
concentrate on finding the
remaining one.
Haruka!
You must give the Holy Grail
to the Legendary Messiah...
Huh?
Legendary Messiah?
Who is that exactly?
A frightening world of
silence is coming.
She is the only one who
can save the world from
destruction.
When the Messiah holds the
Holy Grail, the world...
...will be saved.
No!
"The Holy Grail's Mystical
Power: Moon's Double
Transformation."
She's alive!
It's very faint, but her
heart is still beating!
Okay! There still might be
time to save them!
We have to find a way
to turn the taliman's
back to their original
pure‐heart crystals?
[fright screams]
[gasps]
[nasty laughter]
[gasps] [nasty chuckles] Sorry
ladies, I now possess the
two talismans.
We'll see about that!
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
[nasty chuckle] If you
think I'm gonna let you
take those talismans,
you're totally mistaken!
They're my friends' pure‐heart
crystals! Give them back!
Fire...
...Buster!
[scream]
[laugh] I guess you weren't
expecting that! I'm
just full of surprises today.
So what do you
think of my new and
improved Fire Buster Two?
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Oh no, 'Shine Aqua
Illusion' didn't work!
An eye for an eye!
Fight fire with fire!
Burning...
Mandala!
[fear gasp]
Mars, you've got to stop what
you're doing, right now!
You're just
making the flames bigger!
[laugh]
You might as well give it up!
Your techniques will
never extinguish the
flames of my Fire Buster!
[fright gasp]
I can promise you that,
very shortly, you will
all be burned to a crisp!
[laugh] Bye, now!
If we don't do something
fast, we'll be barbequed!
Luna P! Extinguish!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
And Tuxedo Mask!
[chuckling]
I thought we were done for!
Yeah, seriously!
Guess we got here
just in time!
Thank you so much, Sailor
Chibi‐Moon! And Tuxedo Mask!
Go retrieve those talismans!
Right!
Uranus! Neptune! Hang in
there. I promise you...
...I'll be back, and I'll
return your talismans.
Finally. I've obtained two
of the talismans. Just one
more to go!
You girls don't know
when to give up!
Sticky Ooze!
[gasp]
Huh?
[panic yell]
What is this?
What the heck?!
My legs are stuck!
Oh yeah‐‐‐ ?
[chuckles] So long, suckers!
Don't step in this
stuff, Sailor Moon!
Or you'll never get out!
What do I do now?!
What do I do?!
Eudial's getting away!
[determined grunt]
Sorry, everybody!
Sorry! Pardon me! Heads
up! Coming through!
Look at that! She's just
like the mythical Hare of
Inaba!
I doubt that rabbit
was so heavy!
Are you hurt?
No, but if you let
Eudial get away, you're
gonna be hurting!
You can cut her
off, Sailor Moon!
Go ahead! We'll
catch up later!
[affirmative grunt]
I can't let her escape!
I promised Uranus and
Neptune that I'd save
them, and I will!
I'll retrieve those
talismans and return
their pure‐hearts to
them, no matter what!
You again...
You stomped on people's hearts!
And even had the
nerve to try and take
their precious lives!
You're awful!
I am the Pretty Guardian...
...who fights for Love
and for Justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Hmpf!
You're a tough girl, huh?
Well, I'm not worried. In
case you've forgotten...
I've neutralized your special
attack once already.
One thing's obvious. I'm
clearly superior to you in
strength.
If you don't want to die, do
yourself a favor, and run
away now! [laughter]
I don't care if you're
stronger than me! I'll take
back those talismans, if
it's the last thing I do!
Moon Spiral...
Fire...
Heart Attack!
...Buster!
[gasp]
[laugh] It's not like I
didn't warn you...
Since our last battle, I
went back and made further
modifications to perfect my
Fire Buster's power to destroy.
In other words, your puny
attack will never work
against me.
[nasty laughter]
Sailor Moon Super!
Sailor Moon, you've gotten
in my way too many times.
Today, I'm gonna pay you
back. And believe me, it'll
be a pleasure.
Fire...
Stop right there!
Huh?
And just who are you?!
Setsuna Meioh!
Eudial, I demand that you
return the talismans right
now.
Are you crazy?!
Sailor Moon!
Who is she?
Pluto Planet Power Make Up!
Sailor Pluto?!
Puu! Is that really you?!
Hello again, Sailor
Guardians.
Why are you here?
Because I hold...
...the last talisman!
[gasp]
[chuckle] How convenient.
Well...
Thank you for saving me the
trouble of having to go find
that thing.
I will not allow the
talisman to remain
in the hands of an
evil being like you.
Return!
[gasp]
Uranus!
Neptune! Wha‐‐‐?
Look, their pure heart
crystals are...
...being returned to them!
Thank goodness!
The three talismans!
Incredible, and no one had
to be sacrificed.
Amazing! The talismans
possess truly magical
powers!
[amazed gasp]
[cries of terror]
What? What's
happening here?!
That Holy Grail is
set possess infinite
power. Depending on who
wields this item...
...it can lead the world
to either peace or
destruction.
That Holy Grail...
Is going to be mine!
[painful groaning]
[laughter]
[screaming]
You're not getting
the Grail!
Out of my way!
[painful scream]
[laughter]
[screaming]
She has the Holy Grail!
Sailor Moon!
Is this the Holy
Grail's power?!
Hey, what's going on?
Fire Buster!
[big scream]
What amazing power! Is
she the messiah who
will save the world
from the Silence?
[gasps of amazement]
Curse you, Sailor Moon! I
swear, I'll get you for
this!
Hi Eudial, thought I'd call
to let you know that you've
just been fired.
Mimete?
We've been patient with all
your failures up until this
point, but we've reached our
limit. It's become
unbearable.
What?! How dare yo‐‐
We're ashamed to even admit
that you were a member of
our Witches 5 coven!
So do us all a favor
and die, okay?
Did you say die? That's
absurd! The battle is only
just beginning!
What's wrong with
these brakes?!
What?! 'Death to the Snail
Woman in the station
wagon?!' Mimete!
[fright scream]
Thanks for all
your hard work!
[fear gasp]
Sailor Moon!
Hi, Mamo...
Are you alright, Usako?
You really scared us!
Don't worry, I'm fine,
guys. Just feeling really
tired, that's all...
It looks like we were wrong.
Sailor Moon may not be the
Messiah.
Huh?
The true Messiah would
display unlimited power.
Sailor Moon was exhausted
after this one incident.
Then the true Messiah
is someone else.
If that's the case, it would
seem the two of us have been
given a new mission.
[sobbing]
Ahh... [chuckles]
Professor! The Holy
Grail has appeared!
[chuckling]
Unfortunately, it's in the
hands of the Sailor
Guardians!
[chuckle]
Hm? Did you hear
what I said?
It may be true that the Holy
Grail has finally appeared...
But it seems there is
no‐one among our opponents
who is capable of accessing
its true power...
Hm?
It's obvious, really. If any
one of them could actually
control the Holy Grail...
...this whole story would have
been by now! My Death
Buster's mansion and every
Daimon egg would have been
destroyed long ago!
But take a good look! Not a
single crack in any one of
them!
[crazed laughter]
So, Professor...
[laugh] Hm?
You're saying that we
need someone who can
wield the Holy Grail
for the Death Busters.
Can I assume this person
might be one of us?
Oh yes!
I'm Mimete! I'm a bit of a
klutz, and also a crybaby, but
I'm working hard to become
a big‐time super villain!
Root for me, okay?
This is supposed to be the
next episode preview!
Take your self‐introduction
speech elsewhere!
[giggle] Our Messiah
will awaken soon. So
go ahead, act tough
while you still can!
[laughter]
Next time on Sailor
Moon Super: 'Who is the
True Messiah? Chaos of
Light and Darkness!'
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.