It's finally happening. The
Messiah of Silence is about
to awaken. Is killing
Hotaru really the only
way to save the world
from its destruction?
No! I can't accept that.
I won't let it happen!
There has to be a way to
save everyone without
spilling any blood!
In the name of the
Moon, I will find a way!
'Shadow of Destruction: The
Messiah of Silence Awakens!'
Gather together, students!
Come to Mugen Academy.
Follow my voice...
Do you hear that?
The wind is crying.
It's not just the
wind crying, Haruka.
It's the entire planet.
It's as though they're
being taken over
by an unknown fear.
Chibi‐Usa...
Hotaru...
Where did you go?
Chibi‐Usa...
Hey, cheer up! I
know you're worried
about Hotaru, but I'm
sure she's‐‐‐ [scream]
[gurgles]
Usagi!
Sorry about that!
Payback!
[giggles] So that's the
way it's gonna be, huh?!
You asked for it!
[scream]
‐I won! Yay!
‐Hold still!
Goodnight, now. Don't
forget to dry your hair.
Okay! Oh, Usagi?
Huh? Listen, thanks for trying
to cheer me up back there.
I feel a little better now.
Good.
Good night! See
you tomorrow!
Sleep tight.
Usagi...
[affirmative grunt]
Mugen Academy students are
gathering at the school.
I'm afraid something
bad is about to happen.
I'm sorry for leaving you
behind, Chibi‐Usa. But don't
worry, I'll find and
rescue Hotaru for you.
Chibi‐Usa...
Her condition is
deteriorating faster
than I anticipated.
We must hurry and
get her a pure heart
before it's too late.
Fortunately, I've already
made preparations.
As the last and most
powerful member of
Witches 5, I,
Cyprine, will bring
her the finest
pure heart there is.
Glad to hear that,
Cyprine. But do hurry.
You're the only one I
can count on anymore.
Don't worry sir. I'm
much more competent than
Kaolinite.
I will not let you down.
Yes, let's hope
that is the case.
Professor, those were
the same exact words
you said to me!
Damn you, Cyprine!
[snicker]
If that's how it's going
to be, I'll show them.
I'll obtain the best
pure heart there is!
You'll see, Cyprine!
I already know who has the
purest heart. I'm going to
target that little
girl who's become
Hotaru's closest friend.
The one everybody
calls Chibi‐Usa!
[gasp]
Help me,
Chibi‐Usa. [scream]
Hotaru!
[scream]
Come, gifted students
of Mugen Academy.
Now is the time to
give your pure hearts
to the Death Busters!
Step forward, each of you.
Now's your chance to make
the ultimate sacrifice!
That's it... Offer
your pure hearts!
[gasps]
That's it! Give me
your pure hearts!
[chuckle]
[gasps]
[chuckle] I see you
there, young ladies.
Outsiders aren't
allowed here I'm afraid.
[scream]
Sorry for the disruption.
Everyone okay?
Great. I'm going to step
out for a bit to deal
with those pests. [chuckle]
You ready?
Yes.
Huh?
Where are we?! Welcome to
you all, Sailor Guardians.
[gasps]
[chuckle] My name is
Cyprine, I am the last
and greatest member
of Witches 5.
Well I guess she already
knows our true identities...
Then let's transform!
Venus Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Moon Cosmic Power!
Make Up!
With the power of
love and beauty,
I will save this planet!
I won't permit the evil
silence to happen!
Douse yourself in
water, and repent!
You defile pure hearts!
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
I won't let you have your
way! I'll fill you with so
much regret, it'll
leave you numb!
We are the Sailor Guardians!
And in the name of the
Moon, we'll punish you!
Soon, this planet
will be engulfed by the
Silence. And
then we, the Death
Busters, will be
victorious.
Not if we stop you first!
Burning... Mandala!
I got her!
[gasp]
Sailor Mars!
[scream]
[nasty laugh]
Venus Love Me Chain!
[chuckle]
You're not going anywhere!
You think you've
caught me, do you?
Yeah, I do‐‐ [scream]
[gasps]
[chuckle]
I am Cyprine.
And I am Ptilol.
[gasps]
‐We are one.
‐Body and mind!
Yeah, one pain
in my butt!
Take this! Sparkling
Wide Pressure!
Ptilol!
Cyprine!
Sorry, but...
Your attack
won't work on us!
[scream]
Jupiter!
[screams]
Look at them run
around like cowards!
These Sailor Guardians
aren't really
much of a challenge.
[growl]
Sailor Moon Super!
Hotaru...
Hang on and wait for me.
I'm coming to save you!
Moon Prism Power Make Up!
So she's a Sailor
Guardian, too.
How very convenient.
[chuckle]
[scared gasp]
I'm not afraid! I can do
this! I'm coming, Hotaru!
Hotaru?
Hotaru has been waiting
to see you, my dear.
[gasp]
Your timing is excellent.
Hotaru was just saying
she wants your pure heart.
Tuxedo Mask!
Kaolinite, your heart is so
cold, you can't even feel
this girl's love
for her friend!
You're truly a
pathetic warrior.
[chuckle] Take this!
[scream]
Sailor Chibi Moon!
[nasty laughter]
Dead Scream!
Chibi Moon!
[gasp]
Small Lady!
[evil laugh] Too late!
I have it, the
purest of hearts!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
[gasp]
[scream]
[nasty chuckles]
Damn it!
They're strong!
There must be a
way to defeat them.
It's going to be difficult.
Their teamwork
is too good.
If we could just find a
way to separate them...
Playtime is over, ladies.
Now comes
the real attack.
This time, we'll send
you straight to hell!
Okay then, it's
all or nothing!
Right!
I'm with you!
It's time to show them...
...our teamwork!
Bubble...
Spray!
Believe me, you're
wasting your time.
Venus Love Me Chain!
Ptilol!
Cyprine!
Moon Tiara Action!
Fire Soul!
You might as well stop. Your
attacks don't work on us.
We absorb your powers. All
it really does is make us
that much stronger.
[grunt]
Cyprine!
Damn!
Don't chase after her!
[grunt]
Agh! Damn you!
[laughter] You aren't
getting away!
Why you!
Hmpf! I've got you now!
[gasps]
[laughter]
[laugh]
What?!
Cyprine!
Ptilol!
[screams]
Looks like we did it!
That really was a close one.
[gasp]
I think everything's
back to normal!
Look!
[gasps]
Well, except for that.
What is that
a passageway?
I'm reading it as
an anomaly in space.
It leads to an
alternate dimension.
Could it be the Death
Buster's hideout?
Let's check it out.
Right!
[chuckle]
Welcome, Sailor
Guardians.
I've been expecting
your arrival.
So you've finally
shown yourself.
[chuckle] How fortunate.
You're just in time to
witness our special ceremony.
[gasp]
[gasp] Sailor
Chibi Moon!
[growl]
[scream]
Uranus!
He's created a powerful
force‐field around himself!
Uranus!
Neptune!
[chuckle] Seems as though
everyone made it on time.
Hotaru's dad?! [gasp]
Sailor Chibi Moon!
[chuckle] Kaolinite...
Yes Professor, we are
now ready to awaken
the Messiah of Silence.
All that remains is to
extract the pure heart
from Chibi‐Usa, and
offer its energy.
I can feel it that
pure heart energy.
Chibi‐Usa!
Come back!
[screams]
[groan]
Sailor Moon!
Ah!
[laughing]
The time has now come,
Messiah of Silence!
We've gotta stop them
from taking her pure heart!
[scream] Chibi Moon!
[screaming]
Oh hi, Hotaru.
I'm glad you're alright...
Stop it! Please!
Chibi‐Usa!
Such beauty. A pure
heart, befitting the
Messiah of Silence!
You mustn't do this! If
Sailor Saturn awakens,
this world will be doomed!
No! Don't! Stop it!
Mr. Tomoe, please!
Don't let her do this!
You're Hotaru's father!
If you love her you
have to stop her!
"Love"?
Oh please,
what is that?
[gasps]
[gasp]
Hold on! I've never seen her
before! That's not
Sailor Saturn!
Then who is she?!
I am the true Messiah of
Silence! I am Mistress 9!
[laughing]
What's going on?
I thought Sailor
Saturn was the
Messiah of Silence!
It all makes sense now! The
Death Busters must have
planted something
inside Hotaru years ago!
And nowthat powerful
evil has taken
control of her body!
We did it, Professor.
We've won!
I couldn't have done it
without you, Kaolinite.
Thank you. Those words alone
have made it all worthwhile.
I did it all for
you, Professor.
I love‐‐ [scream]
[screaming]
Professor, why?
Kaolinite has
served her purpose.
Begin preparations
for our next phase.
Yes, Mistress!
Chibi‐Usa!
Grab her quickly!
We all need to get
out of here, right now!
The building is
starting to collapse!
But Usagi and the
others are still inside!
Guys, look!
Sailor Moon!
Chibi‐Usa!
Mamo! They took
Chibi‐Usa's pure heart!
She's not breathing!
What?!
Small Lady, no!
Let's get her
back to my place!
Wait! What about
the other students?!
Don't worry, they've
already been evacuated!
Hurry!
Mamoru and
Chibi‐Usa's bodies are
linked together now.
His life force will keep her
alive. I just wish there was
more we could do for her.
How could I have let this
happen? Chibi‐Usa wouldn't
be in this mess if I hadn't
left her behind! [sniffle]
Setsuna!
I just came to tell you,
I'm going with Uranus
and Neptune to the Mugen
Academy to destroy
the Messiah of Silence.
You can't be serious!
Don't do it! That
girl is still Hotaru!
There's no other way
to save Small Lady.
No, I won't allow another
life to be taken.
I don't want anyone else to
have to suffer. Not Hotaru...
Not Chibi‐Usa,
not any of us!
Usako!
We have to do
what we can.
And right now,
that's to fight.
No matter what it takes.
We must fight for
what we believe in!
The Age of Light
has ended!
Oh great Master Pharaoh
90, I summon thee.
Bring Silence
upon this world!
We won't let that happen,
as long as we Sailor
Guardians are here!
You're wasting
your efforts!
No! We will protect
Hotaru and this world!
We won't let you
take it from us!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'The Coming Terror of
Darkness: Struggle of
the Eight Guardians'.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.