Wait! Just who are you people?
Are you our enemies? Or
are you our friends?
If you're Guardians, then
please, join with us to stop
those Daimons!
We need your help to keep those
Daimons from taking pure hearts
from the innocent!
I am Sailor Moon! And with my
new technique, I'll punish you!
Kaolinite.
Yes, Professor?
What is our main objective
as Death Busters?
To seek and acquire the Holy
Grail and rule the world.
Correct.
And what must we do to
acquire this Holy Grai?
We must seek out three special
talismans that reside within the
pure hearts of three chosen
humans...
...and that will lead
us to the Holy Grail.
Exactly. I've created another
Daimon egg for that very
purpose.
Ahh.
[Evil Laughter]
Excellent. Now go find a heart
that's pure enough to suit our
needs.
"The Rod of Love is Born:
Usagi's New Transformation."
[Birds Chirping]
[Grunting]
Wait! What's happening?!
Oh no! The Silver Crystal's
power is fading out! [Gasps]
What's wrong, studying
got you down?
You working too hard?
Not getting enough
beauty rest?
Usagi, maybe it's time you
retire from being a Guardian.
What?!
Why you! I thought you were my
friends! [Grunting]
[Screams]
I'll never quit! [Grunting]
Snap out of it Usagi!
[Sighs]
It was, a dream?
It was. Must have been a
nightmare.
But it's not just a
bad dream, is it?
Until the light comes back, it's
impossible for me to transform.
Usagi.
Luna, could this really mean
that I'm done being a Sailor
Guardian?
No, of course not!
But what about the Silver
Crystal?
You'll be fine, Usagi.
Everything will be all right.
C'mon! Don't let this
get you down!
I know! Go have a
talk with Mamoru.
Huh?
Go on! Get going
it'll cheer you up!
That sounds like a
bad dream all right.
So Mamo...
What do you think? What am
I supposed to do now?
If I can't transform then I
won't be able to defend Earth
from our new enemy.
[Sighs]
Hmm.
Of course! I know something
that'll make you smile!
Hmm?
Come along now!
Ahh!
[Heavy Breathing]
Umm.
Come on!
Is it okay for us to
even be in here?
I don't know! Who cares!
Oh, there's nobody around!
[Gasps] Now I know what
you're up too, Mamo!
You want to be alone with me!
That's why we're here!
Uhh, don't get
the wrong idea!
It's okay Mamo, don't be
embarrassed. I feel the same
way!
Mmm!
Hmm?
[Screams]
What a cute kitty!
Aww!
[Meow]
Hi!
Aren't you the sweetest
kitty ever!
I say we should
name you sugar!
Okay? So Mamo, did you bring me
here to show me this kitty?
Yeah. I thought you'd like
visiting all the stray cats in
this place.
There's more!?
[Meow]
Oh Sugar where are you going!?
[Heavy Breathing]
Mamo help me find him!
All right. [Chuckles]
[Giggles] Okay everyone, dig in!
Don't worry, take your time.
There's plenty more food
where this came from!
Excuse me, are you taking care
of all those cats?
[Gasps] Who's there?!
I'm the Guardian of cats!
[Giggles]
Hello there!
Huh? [Giggles]
[Giggles]
They're so friendly! So do you
come out here every day to feed
them?
Yeah, I just feel so
sorry for them.
They've been living in this
house, but it's gonna be torn
down soon.
Ohh.
All I want is for them to
be happy and safe.
That's so kind of you.
All right!
I'll help you take care of these
cats and find them all homes!
Mamo, you don't mind, do you?
No, not if this is really going
to make you happy.
[Meow]
[All] What? You're doing cat
rescue now?!
Yep! I'm taking care of them
until I can find them all
new homes!
Rei.
Ami.
Minako.
Mako.
Since I can count on each of
you adopting a cat, that means
four of the cats will have happy
homes!
Hold on, Usagi. I already have
Artemis and he's as much cat as
I can handle.
I'm standing right here.
[Laughing] Oh get over yourself.
And I...Hah!
Have too many birds that live
around here. A cat's out of the
question.
[All] Uhh.
Uh, y'know, I live alone so I'm
never home, I can't take care of
a cat.
Well I...With all the important
school exams that are coming up.
I don't think I could manage a
cat either Usagi.
All the four of you can do is
just think about yourselves,
what is it with you guys!
Well then why don't you let
them all live at your place.
[Grunting]
Well you see I uhh, hmm.
My family can barely get by now
because Luna's such a gluttonous
pig!
Who are you calling
a glutton, you...!
Well I'm sure there are
lots of people out there who
will be happy to adopt them.
Alright, fine! But the least
you girls can do is help me out
by picking up some cat food! Now
get going!
See you soon!
What's gotten into her?
Nothing new. Just
gone cat crazy.
[Heavy Breathing]
You have to stop following me!
[Meowing]
I'm sorry but we're not allowed
to have cats here.
[Meowing]
Alright, but only 'til
my Mom comes.
Hmm.
Now please don't mess
up my room.
No, kitty! Get off my bed!
No! Careful, you're messing up
my puzzle!
Now where did this
piece come from?
[Screams]
Nekonnel!
[Gasps] What's going on here?
[Yells]
[Grunts]
Calm down. I've come here to
collect the talisman that you
have in your pure heart.
[Hissing]
[Screams]
Run kitties!
Oh no you don't!
[Grunting]
[Meowing]
[Heavy Breathing]
[Grunting]
[Sighing]
[Evil Meow]
[Gasps]
[Screams]
I wonder why that girl didn't
come to feed them today.
What a good kitty.
Well maybe I can talk my Grandpa
into adopting one of them.
Why stop at just one? Take a
whole bunch of them with you!
Usagi, this isn't some kind of
bake sale. It's not like they're
cupcakes.
Oh, sorry!
[All Giggling]
Meow!
[Screams]
Where are they going?
[Meowing]
Why'd they all just run off?
[Grunts]
[Gasping]
[Laughing]
[Grunts]
[Screams]
[Meowing]
[Grunting]
[Screams]
[Gasps]
It's another Daimon!
Not sure if this'll work. But I
gotta try!
Moon Crystal Power! Make Up!
[Sighs]
[Both] Usagi!
[Screams]
[Chuckles]
[Gasps]
Alright, let's go!
[All] Mhm!
Mars Star Power! Make Up!
Jupiter Star Power! Make Up!
Mercury Star Power! Make Up!
Venus Star Power! Make Up!
[Screaming]
Scream all you want, no
one can save you!
[All] Stop right there!
Hmm?
[All] The Sailor Guardians have
arrived!
Seriously?
Burning...!
Mandala!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[Screams]
[All Groaning]
I've gotta go help them!
You stop that!
No don't!
Usagi no!
[Screams]
[Groaning]
[Grunts]
Good. There's no one else to
interfere.
[Chuckling]
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
Hmph!
Hmm. And now to present this
pure heart to Lady Kaolinite.
[Gasps]
[Screams] What the nel?!
[Screams]
She wasn't much of a challenge.
[All] Hmm?
It's those same two
from last time!
Well then?
No. This isn't a
talisman either.
Thank's for saving
us. Who are you?
[Gasps]
[Gasps] Hold on!
You haven't defeated the enemy
yet! If you're Guardians like
us...
...Then let's fight
them together!
Don't get the wrong idea.
Our only objective is
obtaining those talismans.
We're not looking to
team up with anyone.
That's right, you need to solve
your own problems yourselves.
[Laughing] Meow!
[Gasps] What the!
[Screams]
[Grunting]
[Laughing]
[Groaning]
Please just stop!
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
[Grunting]
Meow!
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
Hey, who did that?!
Tuxedo Mask!
Those who dare to toy with the
pure of heart, will one day find
themselves judged by those who
are pure.
Nekonnel!
[Gasps]
Hmph!
Meow!
[Chuckles]
What?
Hmph!
[Gasps]
Meow!
[Grunts]
Tuxedo Mask, you're hurt!
Run, Usako!
Meow!
[Grunting]
Now Usako! Get moving! You need
to get away from here quickly!
I can't leave you
here alone!
Go now! Hurry!
I can't! I want to protect
everyone!
That includes you,
my beloved Mamo.
No matter what, I will always
fight at your side.
Usako.
Oh Usagi.
Meow!
[Screams]
What's going on?
[Inhales]
Is all this being created
from our combined powers?
Is that the legendary...
Spiral Heart Moon Rod?
The power of our love, that's
what allowed this miracle to
happen.
Nekonnel!
Hmph.
Meow!
Usagi, go! You
need to transform!
And you can
definitely do it now!
Hmph.
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
I can't forgive people who
trample those with a pure heart!
Not now or ever!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and for
justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Meow!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[Screams]
Lovely!
Meow!
I really did it! I transformed!
Excellent! Well
done, Sailor Moon.
[Giggles]
This is ours, right?
Mhm.
I'm so relieved!
But now the real
trouble's about to start.
That's true. You still have to
find homes for all these cats.
[Giggles]
I've already done that.
[All] Huh?
Rei will take five cats, Ami
will take two, Minako two, and
Mako just one!
Usagi! We already
told you we can't!
[Laughing] Knock it off,
I'm not a cat!
[Heavy Breathing]
I know! I'll just take them to
the Great Animal Kingdom!
[Sighs] You kidding me? Why
didn't you think of that sooner?
[Screams]
[Both] That girl's hopeless.
All right! This guy
is all mine!
Whoa, what's gotten
into you Minako?!
I have finally found Mister
Right! Oh my darling! [Giggles]
Alright, I get it. But it
seems that your Mister Right
already has a lovely girlfriend.
Who cares! My heart
burns for his love!
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"A Handsome Boy? Haruka
Tenoh's Secret."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.