If you have a dream, no
matter how unrealistic it
may seem right now, you
can make it come true if
you really believe in it.
Just hold that dream
in your heart, change
your evil ways, become a
truly good person,
and you know what,
Mimete? You can be a
star of the future!
Where is that pure heart?
You must hurry.
Give me a pure heart.
A heart that will
make me complete.
Messiah of Silence.
My most talented subordinate
is putting a plan into
action to accomplish
that as we speak.
We'll have that pure heart
here for you soon, I promise.
♪ Ooh, yeah I stop,
and turn around! ♪
♪ And I can hear someone
calling out my name. ♪
♪ Could it be anxiety? Or
just crazy, hazy love‐‐‐ ♪
Our next song by your
favorite artist is one
you've all been waiting for!
That's right! It's Jinta
Araki's new single: "Blue
Crisis Love!"
Oh, Jinta! I love you!
"I Love Idols:
Mimete's Dilemma"
[cheering]
That's crazy.
Like ants in a
pile of sugar.
Don't those fan‐girls have
anything better to do?
Fan‐girls? Girls obsessed with
their favorite celebrities.
Some even follow them
all over the world!
What would they do if they
caught up with them?
Oh they just want
to be near them.
Just thinking about all that
running around and screaming
wears me out. I
don't understand why
anyone would
do it. Do you, Minako?
Minako?
Huh? Wha‐What?
You look like you
were daydreaming.
Oh! Really?
You're not turning into
one of those rabid fans,
drooling all over that guy.
No! Who is he?
You know perfectly well.
It's Jinta Araki‐‐‐
Who has time to get
obsessed with pop stars?
Never even heard of him.
Get your hand off my face!
[grunting]
So you have an
announcement to make?
Yes. I'd like to have
someone who is watching
right now play my heroine
in a blockbuster
movie that will be
shooting this summer.
First round of auditions
will start at 4:30 pm
tomorrow, at the Minato
Cultural Center.
Part of the audition is
looking good in a swimsuit.
So wear your favorite
suit, and get ready
for some stiff
competition!
I'll be waiting, ladies‐
Hey!
What?
I don't understand
this sentence...
Seriously?
Ahh...
Mimete...
Our Messiah of Silence is
growing tired of waiting. I
hope you're making progress
coming up with a new plan.
Of course! Take a
look at this‐‐‐ Ah!
Here, a photo of the
young man who's going
to be our next target.
Oh? This is Jinta Araki,
also known as Alazin.
He's eighteen, with
an irresistible smile.
He has a new single
on the charts and
it's only a matter of time
before it's at the top.
So he's a singer?
Listen, Mimete. It's
becoming clear that you're
more interested in meeting
famous people than in
stealing their hearts.
Those who are unable to
separate work from play,
will never succeed
as a Death Busters.
[gasp] Oh no!
Y‐ You're mistaken!
I'm totally dedicated!
I choose famous people
because they have more
charisma than other people.
And because of that I figure
that their hearts would be
more effective at
awakening the Messiah.
Saying that I'm playing
around makes me want to cry.
[sobbing]
Oh, no need to cry. I was just
concerned because I believe
you could have a promising
future here with me.
Really?
I'm counting on you to
work hard, Mimete. Okay?
Yes, sir!
You'll be a great villain
one day. Trust me.
I'll do the very best I can!
That's what I like to hear.
Hm...
"I love, love, Araki."
I hope your heart crystal is
even better than your tan.
[laugh]
And next, you substitute
the 'X' with this.
Mm‐hm.
Wow, that is amazing,
Usagi. You understood that?
Not at all!
[groan]
Where's Mina? She said she was
running a fever, so she
went home to rest.
Wha‐?
I know what she's up to!
[buzz of conversation]
Well, here I am.
So far so good.
If I can just see him in
person, I'll tell him
what a big fan I am.
E‐Excuse me?
Mm?
Uh, I was wondering.
Do you know what time
Jinta Araki will arrive
for today's auditions?
According to the schedule
I've been given, he's not
going to be here today.
[gasp] But he'll be coming to
watch the second round
of judging tomorrow.
What?!
Oh, no!
Huh?
But I came all this way
today just to see him...
Hm? No way!
This is unbelieveable!
[grunting]
This!
Is the very first T‐shirt
they made of him.
We both have a
collector's item.
Pretty cool.
Yeah. We're both
devoted fans.
I'm Minako Aino.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mime‐ I mean, Mimi
Hanyu. It's nice to
meet you too!
Auditions are
about to begin.
Last chance to sign up!
[grunt]
Let's take that chance. If
you want to realize your
dream, you've got to give
it everything you've got!
Yeah!
Thank you.
Next, please.
Hi! My name is Minako Aino.
I'm a fifteen year
old middle school
student full of energy!
I'm great at all sports,
especially volleyball!
Some of the scenes in the
movie will require kissing.
How do you feel about
making out on camera?
I'm okay with it. I just
won't tell my parents in
case they freak out,
but I think kissing is
the best part
of acting!
[laughing]
If you're chosen for the
part and the director
invites you to dinner...
What would you do?
Oh, that would be fine. I'm
not a picky eater! I don't
have to have gourmet food.
I'll eat anything
placed in front of me!
Oh, but well... I'm not a big
fan of shitake mushrooms.
[laugh]
Thank you.
Next, please.
Okay, hi. Um,
I... I'm Mi‐‐
Mimi Hanyu. I'm very
glad to be here.
Why don't you tell
us why you came to
this audition today.
Uh... Well... Um... Uh‐h‐h!
Just take your
time. But faster.
I'm so sorry.
Um, oh, um...
That's enough.
Thank you.
Mm‐mm‐mm.
The first round of judging
is now concluded.
The following
five participants
have been selected.
Number Twenty‐Four....
Only five will
come back tomorrow.
I doubt we'll get called.
Aw! Just once, I wanted
to see him up close.
Number Two Fifty‐One.
[grunt]
[gasp]
Amazing!
And lastly, Number
Two Fifty‐Two!
[scream]
Those who were selected,
please come forward!
These girls will be moving
on to the second round of
judging tomorrow. As you
already know, the winner
will appear with Jinta Araki
in a movie scheduled to be
released next year.
Sailor Moon Super!
What if they pick
me? I wonder,
could that
really happen?
What if my dream
actually comes true?
Well I'm ready for anything!
I've got the good looks!
And a terrific bod!
No human can
outshine me.
I've set my mind to
aim for the top!
[laugh]
[cheering]
My Mimete!
I'm so proud!
Professor! You
came to see me!
I'm so happy you're here!
Can you hear me?
Yes, sir.
Mm...
You're running a slight
fever, and your eyes are
bloodshot, as well.
It's good to be dedicated
to your work, but
don't neglect your health.
It would be especially
problematic right now, if an
excellent worker like
you called in sick.
U‐Understood, sir!
I got so wrapped up in my
dream of fame, I completely
forgot my assignment
was to steal Jinta's
pure heart crystal!
And if I do that, I'll be
killing my favorite idol.
[sigh] Why did I decide to
choose my beloved Jinta.
He's gonna die...
[gasp] Worse than that, the
second round of auditions
will be cancelled. There'll
be no movie contract.
And my chance for
stardom, gone!
[groan]
On the other hand, if I
don't go after Jinta, my
future here will be dead.
I'll be branded a traitor.
Just when I'm apparently
getting so close to
becoming a top executive.
[whining]
You'll be a great villain
one day. Trust me.
Let's take that chance. If
you want to realize your
dream, you have to give
it everything you've got!
Yep! She's right! I don't care
about the Death Busters anymore!
Not when I have a chance
to spend the summer
in Jinta's arms!
I'll do whatever it
takes to be with my idol.
Even if I have to betray
this organization.
I was never cut out to be
a super villain anyway.
When you get right down to
it, I'm a good person at heart.
I'm sure you're all
interested in who will
become the heroine.
That's why I'd like everyone
here to participate
in that choice.The
young lady who
wins eighty percent
approval from
you, the audience, will
be my lovely co‐star.
Let's begin!
[applause]
[meow]
Is that you, Artemis?!
How did you know
where to find me?
I'm pretty good at figuring
you out, but why aren't
you telling your friends?
Well, I didn't
want to have to admit
to everyone that
I've always been a
devoted Jinta fan‐girl.
Tabulating the votes.
Now!
Sorry, you're out
of the running.
Next up is Number
Sixty‐Eight.
[big breath] Just
two ahead of me.
What happens if you win? Ha!
Then the
world will get a
taste of a Pretty
Guardian Teen Idol!
What?!
Hey, scram!
This morning I
woke up early...
And treated myself to a
big breakfast to prepare
for this audition.
I'm determined to win
because acting is my
greatest passion.
I love it. I can
play almost any role.
No matter what it
takes to get there.
I'm ready to
pursue my dream!
And today, I'm gonna
give it my all!
May the best girl win.
Sorry, my dear. Next up is
number Two Fifty‐One.
Okay!
I'm number Two
Fifty‐One, Minako Aino.
I'm a third‐year
student at Shiba Koen
Middle School in Minato.
Well...Didn't expect to
see her here.
I hope you'll consider me.
Oh, almost! Good try!
Will our next participant
please come forward!
[applause]
Good luck.
Thanks. Darn... So much for my
dream of becoming a Pretty
Guardian Teen Idol.
But I still may have a
chance of meeting Jinta.
You never know!
Minako, right?
Huh?!You were close, but I'm
sure there'll be other
chances for you.
It's really you!
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna be
your fan forever!
That's very nice. But you'll
forget about me someday.
And I don't mean just you.
Everyone will forget
me. But that's okay.
The memories of how
you felt will remain.
I don't mind being a memory.
That's how it should be.
You see, once girls learn
about true love, they move
on from following
celebrities and focus their
feelings on someone who
will be more than a memory.
[sigh]
But for now I appreciate
having your loyal support
though I don't plan on
being remembered as just
a mere teenage idol.
T‐ This morning...
I treated myself to a big
breakfast, and in the future
I want to follow my dream of
becoming a great actress
who can handle any role.
Please vote for me. It
really means a lot.
Our final heroine contender.
I'm now tabulating
the votes.
[gasp]
[gasps]
I won!
[groaning] Oh, so close!
[scream]
Unfortunately, we
don't have a winner.
Thank you all for participating
in these auditions.
Mimi, are you all right?
[gasp]
Uh, Mimi?
[chuckling]
[gasps]
I'm Mimete of the Death
Busters, and you who didn't
vote for me are going
to be very sorry!
I'm going to steal your
beloved idol's pure heart!
Daimon U Tahime,
show yourself!
La‐la‐la‐la‐la‐
la‐la‐la‐La‐a!
U‐Ta Hime!
Charm.... Buster!
[grunting]
[laugh] Looks like everyone's
stunned by my charm!
They appear to be suffering.
U Tahime! [grunt] Sorry. You're
right, they're truly stunned.
Agh! Just go get Jinta!
Okay.
La‐la‐la‐la‐la‐
la‐la‐la‐La‐a !
[grunting]
J... Jinta!
Moon Tiara Action!
[scream]
Hey, who did that?! That
really hurt you know!
Everyone likes to
listen to music.
It's an art that brings
people together!
How dare you silence
an idol's voice!
We are the Pretty Guardians...
Who fight for love
and for justice!
And now in the name of the
Moon, we'll punish you!
Everyone's here.
Venus Star Power!
Make Up!
Mimete!
You pretended to be a loyal
follower of Jinta, and said
you admired him! But look
what you did to our idol!
You're an enemy
to all his fans!
I'm Sailor Venus!
In the name of Venus,
I will punish you!
With the power of love!
You've got it wrong. I
wasn't pretending one little
bit about Jinta. But the
truth is, I am Mimete
of the Witches 5.
Huh, then you really are
a Jinta Araki fan‐girl?
That's none of
your business.
[giggle] He may never sing
again, but Jinta's heart
will belong to us forever.
[giggling]There are unspoken
rules to be followed by all true
fan‐girls. You're
not supposed
to create any problems
for the idols you adore!
[gasp] Jinta's going to die!
Duh! Of course he is! We're
called Death Busters!
We're an evil
organization!
U Tahime, give them a
musical send‐off.
Wipe them out with
your Killer Song.
My pleasure! [clears throat]
La‐la‐la‐la‐la‐la‐
la‐la‐la‐a‐a‐a!
Hurry up! We haven't
got all day!
In order to sing perfectly,
I need to do my vocal
warm‐up. I'll be ready
in just a moment.
Ah‐hah‐hah‐hah‐ha.
Ehh...
Enough already!
Alright, my Killer Song!
I seem to have
forgotten the lyrics.
Unbelievable!
Sailor Moon,
now's your chance!
Yeah!
Crisis Make Up!
Rainbow Moon Heartache!
Oh! I just remembered!
Love is.. Love
i‐i‐i‐is...
Love! Lovely!
I'll be taking this!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[scream]
I'll get you for this!
Looks like the enemy
is still trying to
collect pure hearts.
Why would be the
point of that?
Pure hearts can be turned
into powerful energy that
can change this world.
Huh? It's possible that they've
already found the Evil One,
the Messiah of Silence,
who needs these hearts.
[gasps]
Here.
Huh? I think you should be the
one to give it back to him.
You've been a fan of
his since you were
thirteen, right?
Artemis came and told
us the whole story!
It's okay. [laugh] Big
blabbermouth cat!
Hmph!
I'm sorry professor,
but I'm here to report
that I've failed.
I was so close.
I could almost
taste it. I'm sorry!
[crying]
[gasp]
Well... There's
always tomorrow.
Dreams don't
happen overnight.
The wind is rustling. Listen
to me, Bun‐head. You must
not let the little one go
near Hotaru Tomoe!
But why? Hotaru is
a very sweet girl.
And I just can't bear
to keep them apart.
Chibi‐Usa loves her.
Please just do as
I say. I'm sensing
there's something
very dangerous about her.
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "Shadow of Silence:
The Pale Glimmer
of a Firefly."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.