Now that our long, tough
battle is over, it's
time to kick back and
relax!
Like that's gonna happen!
I'm so behind on my schoolwork
that I need to do some serious
studying if I wanna get into
the same school as my friends!
But how will I find time
when we have a new enemy
to deal with?!
Ah, it's making me crazy!
In the name of
the Moon I'll
punish you!
[startled gasp]
The Silence has begun
to close in.
I'm no match for it!
[shocked gasp]
Are you the Messiah?!
[gasping]
If so, then please,
help us!
[fearful yell]
No, wait!
[gasping desperately]
[fearful inhale]
"Premonition of the
Apocalypse: The
Mysterious New
Guardians Appear."
[startled gasp]
[snoring]
[frustrated reaction]
What is it, Rei?
What's the matter?
Sounded like you were
having a nightmare.
Sorry, guess I must've
drifted off.
I had this really
strange dream.
[yawning in the background]
What did you dream about?
[cheerful laughter]
It was completely crazy
and really funny, too!
I had eaten way too
much ice cream and so
I had to be taken to
the hospital!
And guess who else
was also there?
Mamo! He ate so many
pork buns that he
got sick too!
So we ran into each
other in the hospital
kitchen looking
for more food!
Don't you think
it's funny?
Yes, but we really don't
have time for dreaming
right now. We need to
focus on our studies.
Speaking of that, how did
you do on yesterday's
test, Usagi?
[nervous laughter]
Well, it could've been
worse. At least I didn't
score a zero.
How are you gonna
to pass the entrance
exam for high school?
This is our last
year you have to
do better.
I know...
I wish we could get
back all the study time
we lost fighting evil.
But there's no use
crying over spoiled
milk!
Mm‐hm...
[aggravated groan]
Talking to Minako is
clearly not gonna
help you get smarter!
Minako, the saying is
spilled milk, not spoiled.
Well...that's one way
to say it!
In my opinion, spoiled
really seems to make
a lot more sense.
I know, right?
Just like it sucks when
you look inside the
fridge and find your
milk is spoiled!
I hate it when
that happens.
It's just wrong,
okay?
Ami, can you help
me solve this equation?
Of course, it's simple.
[surprised reaction]
[cynical laughter]
Hm...
Come in here, Kaolinite.
Yes, Professor.
The first Daimon
egg is complete.
I am now sending it forth
to seek the chosen ones
and steal away their
pure hearts!
Pure hearts?
That's right! There are
three humans who possess
pure heart crystals.
The Holy Grail will only appear
once the three talismans
from these chosen humans have
been brought together
Then I will finally get
what I want. I will have
control over everything!
So you're saying that if
we find these chosen people
and obtain their
talismans...
...then we can claim
the Holy Grail and the
world will be ours!
[sinister laughter]
[upset yelling]
This isn't good!
[defeated groan]
No two ways about
it. I got a miserable
score!
I wonder what mom and
dad are going to say
when they see it?
What's worse...if
Rei, sees it what'll
she say?
I don't know why, but
at times like these I
always seem to bump
into Rei...
Ow!
Usagi!
My poor head! Feels
like I hit a tree. Why
didn't you move?
Why didn't you watch where
you were going? You plowed
into me so hard I feel
beaten up!
Move!
Huh! Guess I'd feel
beaten up too if I got
a score like yours on
a test.
How does she
always know?!
But try not
to stress out
about your test
scores so much.
You have lots of good
points, even if schoolwork
isn't one of them.
Huh? You really must
have hit your head hard...
You think so?
By the way Usagi,
do you ever think
about your future?
Huh?
To tell you the truth,
I'm still not sure what
I wanna do. What about
you, Rei?
Well, um I wanna be a
singer‐songwriter, a model,
a famous voice actress and
ah, well...one more thing...
So, what is it?
[nervous laughter]
Don't ask me
about that!
[yelp of pain]
[nervous laughter]
I want to fall madly in
love and get married.
But I would never
admit that!
[giggling]
Uh, you just did.
Usagi, you want to marry
Mamoru one day. Isn't
that your big dream?
Oh, c'mon you're putting
me on the spot it's
really embarrassing!
I'll bet Mamoru would be
embarrassed if he saw that
low score on your test.
Ouch! Sucker punch!
Of course, grades
aren't everything.
...But you'll need to study
harder to keep up with the
rest of your class and have a
bright future with Mamoru.
See ya later!
And stay positive, Usagi!
That's the best thing
you've got going for you.
Man...
[taken‐aback reaction]
Sometimes she says mean
things. But in her heart,
she genuinely cares about
all of us.
She just wants me
to work harder.
Thank you, Rei.
[sinister giggle]
It appears the Daimon
egg located a pure
hearted person in
that shrine.
[displeased groan]
Rei's right. I have
got to do better
than this.
[sigh]
I can already hear
what Mamo would say
if he ever saw this.
That's really terrible.
That's what he'd
say all right,
[startled scream]
[confused sigh]
[nervous laughter]
Nice weather
we're having!
Usako...
The other girls and I
are just gearing up to
really buckle down
and study.
In fact, we're gonna
have a study session
at Rei's place later.
You should've been doing
that all along.
We were too busy saving
the world before. But now
we'll make up for that
lost time.
Okay, then we shouldn't
date until you catch
up on schoolwork.
[dumbstruck reaction]
That's extreme. I don't
think we have to do that...
Here you go.
Study hard.
Thanks.
See ya later.
Yeah.
[nervous reaction]
[upset whine]
Me and my big mouth!
What was that
dream trying
to tell me?
Rin‐Pyo‐To‐Sha‐Kai‐
Jin‐Retsu‐Zai‐Ze!
[small struggle]
It's no use.
I can't sense
anything.
[defeated sigh]
Maybe the dream
meant nothing
at all.
Hmmm...Number
twenty‐seven...
[struggling sounds]
May only good things
happen...and may
everyone live in peace.
[startled reaction]
What the...?!
[fearful gasp]
Mikuuji...
[gasp]
What do you want?!
You care about family
and friends. That's a
sign your heart is pure
and I want it.
If I confront her here,
I'll put grandpa and
the others in danger.
[heavy breath]
[sinister chuckle]
[heavy panting]
[scared reaction]
[stunned gasp]
Your fortune today
says you'll be
having very bad luck!
Daimon Mikuuji, I need
to see if there's a
talisman inside that girl.
Take her heart so
we can find out.
A Daimon...?
Mikuuji!
[terrified gasp]
[painful screaming]
We'll know soon enough
whether she has it or not.
Meanwhile, I'll go find
others who might possess
the talismans as well.
[struggling in pain]
I don't wanna waste
my time studying a
bunch of boring stuff.
I wanna go on
a date with Mamo!
You can't right now.
Yep! That's what
I'm gonna do.
[outrageous yelp]
Usagi! You promised
everyone, including Mamoru,
that you were really
going to study!
No!
Go study or
get the claw!
[scared reaction]
Okay, I'll go then!
Luna, you just don't
understand what it's
like to be a young girl!
You mean what it's like
to be a lazy young girl?
[distant scream]
[startled gasp]
That sounded a
lot like Rei!
What could be
happening?
[painful screaming]
W‐What is that thing?!
I don't know,
but you'd better
transform right now!
Yeah!
Moon Crystal Power...
Make Up!
[evil snickering]
Stop what you're doing!
I am the Pretty
Guardian...
...who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon?
How dare you attack my
best friend who has a
pure heart. That's
absolutely unforgivable!
Now, in the name of
the moon...I'll
punish you!
Hah! A pure heart
is precisely what
I'm here for.
What?!
That thing steals
pure hearts?!
Your fortune says...
[startled yelp]
...very bad luck!
[painful yell and grunt]
Hmph!
[shocked gasps]
What the hell is
that thing?!
A monster!
We're gonna have to
fight it. Let's
transform!
Your fortunes
are the same!
[painful gasps]
Very bad luck!
[struggling sounds]
She's strong!
That's a level of
strength we've
never seen before!
[evil chuckle]
I think it's about time
I dispose of all you
troublesome girls.
[fearful gasp]
[nasty chuckle]
Who did that?!
In the height of Spring,
you're an unwelcome
evil‐doer...
...bringing stormy
weather to a perfectly
pleasant sunny day.
Away with you!
How about I tell
your fortune, too?!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Right!
Moon Princess Halation!
Bad Luck Triangle!
[shocked gasps]
This is your
unluckiest day ever!
[fearful yell]
[scared gasp]
This can't be
happening!
Sailor Moon...
Usako!
[startled gasp]
Looks like your fortune
says bad luck, too.
Tuxedo Mask!
I can't take
it anymore!
Luna!
Stop this!
Enough!
[painful yells]
[painful grunts]
Artemis!
Luna!
I trust there's no
one else who wants
to get in my way?
Now I can take my
time to remove that
girl's pure heart.
[worried breath]
[grunt]
[painful screaming]
Stop!
No. Rei!
Oh no!
[struggling gasps]
Rei, wake up!
You can't die!
You just can't!
By the way Usagi, do
you ever think about
your future?
Well, um I want to be a
singer‐songwriter, a model,
a famous voice actress and
ah, well...one more thing...
[giggle]
I want to fall madly
in love and get
married. But I would
never admit that!
[giggle]
And stay positive, Usagi!
That's the best thing
you've got going for you!
[shaky breath]
Bye, Usagi.
[soft breath]
Don't leave us.
[quiet sobs]
[evil laughter]
I've finally got her pure
heart in my hand, and I
expect there will be a
talisman in it.
[heavy gasp]
Give it back!
Give Rei back
her heart!
You can't do
this to her!
[sobbing]
Hmph!
Human beings are
so pathetic‐
[painful screaming]
What was that?!
What just happened?!
What the hell is
going on?!
[painful screaming]
[shocked gasp]
[surprised reactions]
[stumbling effort]
[fearful gasp]
Rei! Rei! Please be
all right, please
wake up!
Rei!
[panting]
Don't die!
Rei! Can you hear us?
She's not breathing!
There's no talisman
here.
Seems they chose
the wrong heart.
Yeah, it looks
that way.
Come on, Rei...
Say something...
[quiet crying]
[startled gasp]
[shocked gasps]
Are you...?
[soft breaths]
[relieved sighs]
Thank goodness
she's awake!
Why are you all
staring at me
like I died or
something?
[soft sobs]
Rei's finally back
to her normal mean self.
[crying]
Thank goodness!
Usagi...
[loud crying]
Do you feel
kind of woozy?
No, I feel fine.
Any discomfort
at all?
No!
You sure you don't
itch somewhere
or something?
No, not really.
Huh? Wonder who
those two are?
But don't you want
something to eat?
I'm fine, really.
Come on, you can
stop crying, Usagi.
[whimpering]
So, Kaolinite, you're saying
that our target did not
possess the talisman?
No. And there was
unexpected interference.
I'll be more careful
next time.
It seems our new
enemy is hunting down
people with pure hearts.
But that strange creature
said something about
looking for a talisman.
Plus, we don't know
how that mysterious pair
are connected to this...
Well...One thing's
clear. A new battle
is about to begin.
Mamo, I'm thinking
that I might quit
being a Sailor
Guardian.
Nonsense! Chin up,
Usako. I'll protect you.
Mamo, get out of
the way! Look out!
Run Usako!
Save yourself!
Please Silver Crystal!
Give me the power to
protect the ones I love!
Next time on Sailor
Moon Super: "The Rod
of Love is Born: Usagi's
New Transformation."
The moonlight is
a messenger of love.