A romantic first kiss with
the person you love...
It's every girl's dream.
How dare you target
a pure heart that
dreams of that
first kiss!
I'll never forgive you for
being so insensitive and
trampling on a young
girl's fantasy!
In the name of the
moon, i'll punish you!
[dramatic yawn]
I have another study session
at Rei's place. Learning
is so boring!
What are you
complaining
about now?
Huh?
Quit trying to avoid
the inevitable. You've
gotta get going!
You don't wanna make
everybody angry with
you again, do you?
No...But
it's hard!
Studying on a nice
day like this...
It's unfair! I feel
like I'm wasting my
precious youth,
and for what y'know?
Fine, do what you want,
but don't come crying
to me later.
[heavy sigh]
I wish I were on
a date
with Mamo
right now!
Hm?
[excited yell]
It worked! My
wish came true!
Mamo!
Usagi! What
about studying?!
Mamo!
[giggling]
[surprised breath]
Wait, who's that?
"Protect the Pure Heart:
The Three‐Way Battle!"
Mamo, who is that
girl with you?
Hey, Usako!
[surprised breath]
Unazuki?
Hi Usagi! How
are you doing?
Uh, why are you...
with Mamo?
Oh...Because
Motoki is such
a scatterbrain!
He's going on a trip,
but he ran out of the
house and forgot to
bring his ticket!
I came running down
the steps, and there
was Mamoru!
It was perfect timing.
I was just riding by!
I asked him if he had
time to take me to the
train station.
Ohh, that's why! You
guys nearly gave me
a heart attack!
Huh?
What do you mean?
Boy! What a relief!
Oh, nothing really!
[laughing]
It's not important!
Mamo, you look pretty
sharp in that outfit!
Like a professional
driver!
It really shows
off your muscles.
Really? You
think so?
Well you're in such great
shape, everything looks
good on you.
Oh, stop.
[chuckling]
What?! You're asking
if Mamo and I have
kissed?
Come on, Usagi! Keep
your voice down will ya?
[nervous sounds]
So? Be honest. What's the
deal with you and Mamoru?
Have you kissed?
Have we? Uh...
Well, you know...
[giggling nervously]
Oh boy!
Calm down...
That's a very
personal question!
I can see from the
way you're blushing
that you haven't.
[nervous breath]
So tell me, do
you want to?
What?!
Uh...Wait! You've
got it wrong!
It's okay, I understand.
You're both waiting until
you're old enough to kiss,
right?
[stunned yelp]
I mean, what college
man would kiss a fourteen‐
year old?
Uh...Yeah, of course,
you're right. Mamo
is very patient with me.
I guess you know
all about kissing
since you're already
in high school!
You've probably kissed
a bunch of boys!
Huh?
Usagi, can I tell
you a big secret?
Hmm?
Don't tell anyone...
Mmm?
See. there's this boy
I'm dating that I really,
really like.
[anxious hums]
But you see, up to now,
we've never kissed.
[stunned reaction]
What?!
Why not? What are you
talking about?
If you like him why haven't you
kissed him yet?
Because...I want
to cherish my first
kiss forever.
I've thought a lot
about it!
I've got to be
completely in love!
And it's gotta happen
at the perfect time
and place.
So, I'm waiting. Isn't
that how it should be?
[sigh of disbelief]
[small chuckle]
Huh?
Haruka!
Michiru!
[amused chuckle]
Oh, you girls dreaming
of a kiss. How cute.
Oh, I don't know.
I think it's romantic.
I don't suppose you girls
happen to know who shared
the world's first kiss?
Uhh...
Some people believe
the world's first kiss
was between Adam and Eve.
[dreamy breaths]
You know, there are
different types of
kisses.
A kiss on the hand is one of
respect, while a kiss on the
forehead signifies friendship.
And a kiss on the
palm is asking
for a favor.
Wow. You sure know a
lot about kissing.
Do you know what happened
during Medieval Times?
In fifteenth‐century Italy, if
a young couple happened to get
caught kissing,
their families
required them to get married.
Whoa...
Talk about strict!
[pleased chuckle]
A first kiss is magic.
You should cherish it
always.
[small chuckle]
[standing effort]
Bye, ladies.
[dreamy sighs]
Those two are so mature
and sophisticated.
Yeah...
Oh, by the way, Usagi...
I have some delicious
cupcakes at home.
Why don't you bring some
friends to my place later
and we'll share them.
Yeah! Sounds great,
i'll be there!
Good! Well, I really should
get back to work. See ya
later!
Okay! I can't wait I can't
wait! I'm gonna have a
cupcake!
Uh.
I really need to
learn self‐control.
Those girls are
kiss crazy.
I thought their
conversation was sweet.
It's too bad neither
of us have the time to
obsess over love right now.
They're in danger.
Pure and innocent girls
like them...
are very likely
to become targets of the
Daimon.
[alarmed gasp]
Now that I think about
it you're right, Haruka.
I guess we'd better
keep an eye on them.
Kaolinite...
Yes, Professor...
Since your last effort
failed...
Can I presume
that you have found us
a new target?
Yes.
I found a pure‐hearted
girl who's dreaming
of her first kiss.
A kiss? That's something
I haven't done in years.
[sinister chuckle]
[pleased chuckle]
[evil laughter]
[humming]
[relaxed sigh]
That should pretty
much do it.
A first kiss...with
the one I truly love.
Maybe I'm just
too particular.
[startled gasp]
Oosooji!
[terrified scream]
[giggle]
Clean up time!
[whimpering]
Oosooji...Suction!
[painful screaming]
[triumphant laughter]
[screaming]
[satisfied hum]
[triumphant giggle]
The talisman is
now mine!
Not for long it isn't!
Hm?
Who are you?
Answering the call from a
new era,
Sailor Uranus,
here to fight with brilliance!
And Sailor Neptune, here
to fight with elegance!
Ha! That crystal belongs
to me now. There's no way
I'm letting you have it!
Vacuum Cleaner...
Hurricane!
[leaping efforts]
World...Shaking!
[painful gasp]
I've got it!
Oh no, you don't!
[grunting]
Damn it!
Hmph!
Oosooji!
After her!
[frustrated grunt]
Do you see it?
It's gone!
[shocked gasp]
[nervous breaths]
[barking]
[whimpering]
Doggonit!
Unazuki!
I brought some
hungry friends!
You know, all you girls
should be back home
studying right now.
Come on, take it easy.
It's fine! And don't forget,
we're gonna have cake!
Right, and it really
doesn't matter where
we study.
Ami...Are you really
planning to study while
we visit Unazuki?
Of course.
[irritated grunt]
Usagi!
[embarrassed gasp]
Sorry about this! Maybe she's
not back from her part‐time
job yet, or maybe she forgot?
Huh?
That's weird.
[shocked gasps]
Unazuki!
Oh, no!
What happened?
Is she...?
Oh, no...her pure
heart crystal has
been taken!
What?!
We have to find the Daimon
that took it and get it
back quickly!
I know...But it
could be anywhere!
Where is it?! Where?
Where? Where? Where?
Where?
Oh! Found it.
Sometimes sucking
pays off!
[evil laughter]
Have you found
it yet, Ami?
It's within a ten‐
kilometer radius
to the north.
I'm sorry. I can't pinpoint
it any closer than that.
Then, there's no choice.
We'll have to split up
and search.
Be sure you keep
in touch with
one another.
Do you all have your
communicators with you?
Yeah!
[moaning]
Kiss me.
Huh?
Want...a kiss.
[startled yell]
[moaning]
This is weird!
Unazuki, come to
your senses!
No!
Unazuki!
[yell]
Watch out!
Kiss...Kiss...
Try to focus.
Pull it together!
Think back. Didn't you tell me
you wanted to cherish your
first kiss
with the person you
truly loved...
...when the time and
place were perfect?
Don't you remember that?
It doesn't matter who.
I want a kiss!
This is horrible!
Losing her pure‐heart crystal
has completely filled her
mind with impure thoughts!
Wait, say what?!
It has to be what's
going on!
Evil Spirit...
Be exorcised!
[muffled moans]
I'll stick around and
keep an eye on her!
The rest of you, get out
there, find her pure heart
crystal,
and bring it back
here!
[determined grunts]
The question is...
...just where?
Where do we start looking?
That heart crystal could
be anywhere!
Usagi!
According to my instruments,
the Daimon is three kilometers
from your current position.
Everyone needs to head
there now!
All right, I'm on my way!
Mamo!
I heard about Unazuki's
condition, I'll give
you a ride.
Thanks!
[chanting]
[whimpering]
[shocked gasp]
[nervous gasp]
Hurry, everyone!
Please bring back Unazuki's
heart crystal as soon as
you can!
She's not gonna
last much longer
like this!
Usagi, it's right around
that area!
Got it!
What?!
It's inside this place?!
[groan]
How are you still so
loud with the helmet on?
[gasps]
A Daimon!
She's holding a
pure heart crystal!
That must be Unazuki's!
You have to transform!
Right!
Moon Cosmic Power!
Make‐Up!
[grunts]
You two are harder to
get rid of than carpet
stains!
Give up the talisman
right this
minute!
No way! It belongs
to me now!
If you have the guts,
try and take it from me!
That's not going to happen!
I won't let anyone take
that pure heart crystal!
It belongs to a girl who
dreamed of her first kiss
with a wonderful boy!
I won't allow anyone to
steal that pure heart away
from her!
I am the pretty guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the moon, I'll punish you!
Oh, great! Another
ugly dust mite for me
to clean up!
Get ready...
Time to plug that
big mouth of yours!
[scared yell]
Full power!
This blows!
[evil laughter]
[determined grunts]
Time to exterminate
you two!
Eat my dust!
[painful grunts]
[triumphant laughter]
[painful yelp]
[whimpering]
Ow!
Ha! I won't lose this
fight to the likes of you!
[giggling]
[leaping efforts]
[whimpering]
Unazuki...
I have to save her...
...and her dream!
[whimpering]
[painful breaths]
[evil laughter]
Time to blow
you all away!
[shocked gasp]
[startled grunt]
A pure heart will never
be possessed by someone
with a filthy heart!
Return the crystal at once!
Then you can go join the rest
of this garbage heap!
Thank you, Tuxedo Mask!
And...mister horse.
[angry groan]
Now, Sailor Moon...
Show this creature the
power of justice!
[determined grunt]
Right!
Moon...Spiral...
Heart...Attack!
[painful screaming]
Lovely!
[relieved sigh]
[gasp]
Oh, that's right!
I have to get the pure
heart crystal!
Oh no you don't!
[surprised gasp]
[quivering breath]
[startled yell]
We're taking the talisman!
[surprised gasp]
Don't even think
about it!
[leaping effort]
[grunt]
Let go of me! If you
don't let me take that,
Unazuki will die!
We realize there'll
be casualties!
Stop this!
It's wrong!
You don't understand
what's at stake!
She's right! We
have to complete
our mission!
[painful groan]
Whether we like
it or not!
[screaming]
Sailor Moon!
Hold on...This isn't
a talisman!
Again, it's
nothing more than a
pure heart crystal!
What?!
[shaky breath]
Give that back!
[panicked breath]
[uneasy breath]
You can't have this.
It's pure and it's
not yours!
Suit yourself.
[shocked gasp]
What's going
on here?
Sailor Moon!
The Heart Crystal!
Sorry we're late!
Sailor Moon, did
you find it?
Yeah! Come on, let's
all head back to Unazuki's
place!
I wonder if that girl
who dreamed of her first
kiss will be all right?
I'm sure she'll
be fine.
You want to know
the truth?
Hm?
I'm kinda glad that
her pure heart crystal
wasn't a talisman.
What are you saying?!
We have to find those
talismans! It's crucial!
Yes, of course. That's
the mission we were assigned,
and we're going to complete
it, no matter what.
[struggling moans]
[relieved gasp]
Hey, look! She's
coming around!
Thank goodness!
All right! At least now,
she won't be trying to
kiss anyone and everyone!
A kiss should be reserved
for the person you love,
right?
That's right! In the olden
days in italy, if a boy and
girl were caught kissing
they, were forced to get married!
That was the rule for
everybody! No exceptions!
That's how precious a
kiss was considered to be!
That's very interesting
I guess it's only natural that
you would know all about the
history of kissing, isn't it?
Uhh...
Great! Now that you brought
it up,
let's get to work on
some more important history
lessons.
Come on, everybody, it's
time to start our study
session!
What? You seriously want
to study after everything
that just happened?!
Unbelievable!
I'm sorry girls, but if we
don't start now,
we won't be able to
cover today's material.
What a night. Is
Unazuki back to
normal?
Yep. And her precious
dream is still intact.
You mean her first kiss?
That's the one. It'll
still be special.
I have to admit, it makes
me happy knowing I was able
to protect that dream of hers.
[laughing]
I mean, you helped too!
[nervous gasp]
Mind if I ask
you something?
I was just wondering...
Do you remember our
first kiss?
Uh...No...
Sorry.
Really?
You sure?
Come on, think hard!
You've gotta remember!
Look, what's the big deal?
We've kissed plenty of times.
That's ridiculous! A
first kiss should
be precious!
Isn't the moon beautiful
tonight, Usako?
Oh, you're not getting
off that easy!
Uh, look! A monster!
All you people with love
issues, come and see me!
I, Usagi, will fix you
right up!
How are you
gonna help?
I have lots of experience
with relationships!
Don't forget! Mamo
and I have been dating
forever!
Okay, okay...
Rei! You're having
a problem with a boy,
aren't you?
Is it who I
think it is?
I'm not telling you!
Next time on Sailor
Moon Super: Let Moon
Help with Your Love Problems!
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.