Michiru gave me two tickets to
go see a romantic recital with
Mamo! That girl is my idol!
Unfortunately, a Daimon shows up
to ruin this wonderful night!
How dare you intrude on this
special occasion! I won't
allow it!
I am Sailor Moon! In the name of
the moon, I'll punish you!
"Usagi's Idol: The Graceful
Genius Michiru."
[Doorbell Rings]
Mamo!
It's Usako! Are you in there? I
made some tasty cookies! Open
the door!
[Sighs]
Well I made them with love, so
when it comes down to it,
what's one burnt cookie, or three or
four? Or seven? [Laughing]
Hello?
Mamo?
Wow! I never noticed how mature
his apartment was!
"An Analysis of the Future of
Genetic Engineering."
Hmm?
[Laughing]
Of course he has this brainy
stuff! He is a college student!
Oops!
[Screams]
[Gasping]
[Sighs]
What was I thinking? Bringing
him a bunch of burnt cookies.
He deserves so
much better than that.
[Crying]
Huh?
Usako?
I'm pretty
pathetic, aren't I?
Now where's all this
coming from? Huh?
Hmm.
I'm sorry, Mamo! I'm not good
enough to be your future wife!
Now don't cry.
Huh?
[Grunting]
It tastes kinda bitter,
but it's not bad.
Thanks, Mamo.
And don't you ever apologize
for being yourself.
You're the best! [Giggling]
You've gotta be kidding! You
burned all the cookies and
Mamoru ate them anyway?
Mhm!
That poor guy.
Hope he doesn't get
sick to his stomach.
He's perfectly fine!
She's right. I wouldn't
be so worried.
[Gasps] Thank you!
If the cookies were completely
burned through,
there's little chance Mamoru
would get food poisoning.
[Grunts]
[Giggling]
[Grunting]
She's gonna blow!
Everyone! Take cover!
[Gasping]
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
[Giggles] It's fine! I won't get
angry! I feel good today!
Hey Ami.
There's this subject I
want you to teach me.
Like what?
Generic! No, no, I mean, Genetic
engineering!
Oh, oh, and Mako!
[Grunts]
Can you teach me
how to cook?
Why are you so
interested in cooking?
And genetic engineering?
I have made up my mind! I have
to keep up intellectually with
my beloved Mamo!
Minako, can you tell me what it
was like living abroad?
Why?
And you can teach me how to put
on a kimono properly!
That'll cover everything I need
to become the perfect wife!
What's gotten into her?!
I completely forgot! Artemis
needs a bath! I gotta go!
And me as well! I have
to go home now!
But, Mako! Minako!
[Both] See you tomorrow, Usagi!
Oh. [Sighs]
Listen, Usagi. Before you take
on genetic engineering,
you should really study
for biology class...
Don't bother! Usagi isn't
serious! This is just another
one of her crazy ideas.
What's your
problem, Rei?
Mmm!
My problem? That's funny!
I taught you how to put on a
shrine maiden's outfit dozens of
times
and you still couldn't
remember!
You need to grow up and stop
wasting everybody's time!
Mmm!
Hmph!
Maybe you don't waste enough
time! Mmm!
You brought this
on yourself.
Why would Ami or Mako want to
teach you the same things over
and over again...
...when you obviously don't care
enough to pay attention.
The truth is, they've
all given up on you.
[Grunts]
Seriously, I wouldn't be
surprised if Mamoru decided
he didn't want to marry someone
this irresponsible.
Hey, are you even
listening to me? Oh!
[Crying]
I know that, that's why I was
trying to change this time. Why
don't you understand? [Crying]
Alright, take it easy,
Usagi. Oh dear.
Maybe I was a little harsh.
[Crying]
Stupid Luna. Huh?
[Violin Music]
Well, the one thing we do know
is that there's definitely an
evil presence hiding somewhere
in this town.
And when that presence
gets strong enough...
...those damn monsters suddenly
show up here, and attack people!
You must have patience, Haruka.
Until we regain more of our
memories,
we shouldn't expose
ourselves to unnecessary
dangers.
We're here to do a job. And our
mission takes precedence over
everything else.
Not only do we
have to find the three...
...talismans soon, but we have
to summon the Holy Grail and
hand it to its rightful owner.
I understand all that, but it's
so frustrating. Who are these
three pure‐hearted individuals?
How are we supposed
to find them?
Those unlucky souls. The very
act of extracting the talisman,
means death to the owner.
Yes, I agree it's tragic, but it
can't be helped.
When the ultimate goal is to
save the world,
some
sacrifices will have to be
made.
We didn't make the rules. We
just have to complete the
mission we've been given.
[Sighs]
[Violin Music]
[Giggles]
Huh?
Haruka.
Oh, wow! Amazing!
You're just what I think of when
I picture a perfect princess!
Oh, hey Bun‐Head.
Is there something
we can help you with?
I'm sorry I was just so
impressed at how beautifully
you play the violin!
Like a princess, really! I
admire that! It's so inspiring!
[Chuckles]
Oh!
[Violin Music]
[Gasps]
[Chuckles] If you'll
excuse me.
Uhh, where're you going?
I just need some space. It's
time to go for a ride and clear
my mind.
See you around,
Bun‐Head!
Uh, have a good ride. I suppose
I'll see you around. But
stop calling me Bun‐Head!
She's just feeling frustrated.
She knows riding around town
won't solve her problems
but it makes her happy.
[People Talking]
I take it your name
is not Bun‐Head?
No it's not. My
name's Usagi!
I see, Usagi.
Yeah?! [Grunts] Oh.
[Giggles]
So Michiru, are you thinking
of becoming a professional
violinist in the future?
Well, I don't really know.
I'm still searching for my
life's purpose and the path I'm
supposed to be taking.
I'm just not sure.
Wow! You're like me! I don't
really know what to do either!
Excuse me! Are you
Michiru Kaioh?
You painted this
picture, right?
Huh?
[Sighs]
Let me tell you I'm a big fan of
your work!
And I'm really looking forward
to your next exhibition!
Thank you, sir.
She paints, too? No wonder she
doesn't know what to do with her
life. She has so many careers to
choose from!
But I shouldn't be intimidated.
I can do lots of things, too!
[Chuckles] Well, I'm back.
I was hoping to find our enemy
out there,
but it's not gonna be
that easy. At least I had a good
ride to calm down.
Shh!
[Grunts]
[Bad Violin Music]
Oh boy.
Now I see. So that's why you
wanted to learn the violin.
It doesn't matter. I really just
want to play for Mamo, but I'm
not very good.
Perhaps, but don't give up.
You're doing the right thing by
putting in the effort.
I can tell you from personal
experience, that's the only way
people get better.
[Sighs] Thank you.
You know, there's a violin
recital at the concert hall
this evening. Why don't you
use these tickets?
I hope to see you there with
your special someone.
[Sighs] You will!
We are now ready to proceed.
Kaolinite, is everything
in place?
Yes, I found a target.
So now, go forth, Daimon Egg!
And steal a pure heart!
[Giggling] You look charming
in your tuxedo, even without a
mask! I'm so happy.
Usako, are you sure you're not
gonna be bored at this violin
recital?
I'll be fine! As a future queen,
I have to learn to enjoy these
things!
Usagi!
Huh?
Hey, everyone.
Are you guys here to tell
me I'm wasting my time?
Not at all. We're sorry for not
taking you seriously today.
We wanted to apologize, and Luna
told us we could find you here.
I hope that was
all right with you.
We're here to back you up. I'm
personally prepared to pinch
your butt
if I see you falling
asleep during the show.
I brought a copy of the music,
so you can follow along!
Uh, how nice of you!
[Laughing]
Huh?
Oh, there she is. And her date
is pretty handsome, too.
It must be nice
to be so young.
[Chuckles] You're not much
older than she is.
I guess you're right.
[Applause]
[Violin Music]
[Grunts]
[Sighing]
Usagi! Eyes on the stage!
Speak for yourself, Rei! Where
were you looking, huh?!
At the stage! At
the performance!
Shh!
[Giggles]
[Violin Music]
[Screams]
[Grunting]
Usako!
It's awful!
[Grunts]
[Singing]
[Singing] Octave!
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
[Singing] Octave!
Hurry! Get out
of the building!
[Panting]
Usagi!
What's happening?
Octave!
She's here!
Everybody, transform!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Moon Cosmic Power!
[All] Make Up!
[Singing]
Octave!
That's enough!
How dare you show up and destroy
this precious romantic evening
filled with music!
We're not going to
let you get away with it!
We are the Sailor
Team of Justice!
And in the name of the Moon, we
will...
[All] Punish you! Hah!
[Laughing]
Octave!
[Screaming]
I can't move!
[Singing]
[Grunts]
[Grunting]
[Singing]
[Screams]
[Singing] Ow!
Tuxedo Mask, you're here!
Everyone loves a serenade on a
moonlit night.
But the hideous
sounds you're making are nothing
like music!
[Singing]
Octave!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[Gasps]
Be careful! There are a
lot of people still inside
that building!
[Laughing]
She's taunting us!
You jerk! Stop playing
so dirty!
[Laughing] Octave!
[Grunts]
[Singing]
Deep Submerge!
[Screams]
It's them, look!
Answering the call from a new
era, Sailor Uranus, here to
fight with brilliance!
And Sailor Neptune, here to
fight with elegance!
Isn't it time you two Sailor
Guardians tell us who you really
are?
Back off. The last thing we
care about is answering your
questions.
We have a mission with
only one goal, which is
to find the talismans.
Compared to that, everything
else is unimportant.
What do you mean,
'unimportant?'
Well! We thought you were our
allies, but it seems we can't
expect anything from you!
[Grunting]
Huh?
Look out!
Octave!
[Grunts]
Thank you, Sailor Moon.
Uh, sure it was nothing.
So, you wanna play rough?
World Shaking!
[Screaming]
Get her Sailor Moon!
Right! On it!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[Screaming]
Lovely!
Huh. Thanks for stealing
the spotlight.
Uranus.
Hmm?
No. This isn't a talisman. We've
wasted our time here.
Uranus! Neptune!
Give us some answers,
who are you?
And what are the talismans?
[Chuckles] If you want to know
that badly, I guess you'll have
to find out on your own.
The heart of an artist who can
play such a beautiful song has
to be very delicate.
Let's return it gently, alright?
Mhm.
Hey! Wait a minute!
Wow. Those two need
to learn some manners!
Yeah, but I get the
feeling they're good people.
What a shame. We didn't get to
listen to the beautiful recital.
To make up for that, how about
I treat you to dinner?
What?! Alright!
Usagi!
What about all
your training?
Well I guess it'll just have to
wait until tomorrow!
[Sighs]
Mamoru, does that mean you're
gonna treat all of us to
dinner too? How sweet!
Mhm!
Hey, wait a minute! He's my
boyfriend! You can't just invite
yourselves!
Get away from him! I'm serious!
This is not cool! I should have
something to say about this!
Hmm! How cute!
Yeah, guess so!
You have to admit, a romantic
first kiss is every girl's
dream!
You have dreams about
kissing? How cute.
Oh! By the way, Haruka,
who was your first kiss?
That's a secret.
How about you?
Well, mine was uh...
a long time ago.
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"Protect the Pure Heart, The
Three‐Way Battle."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.