Wow, I never knew Motocross
racing was such a competitive
and dangerous sport...
...especially if you're
competing against a bunch of
pros!
But Haruka's a great driver so
I'm sure she'll win the race.
What? The enemy set a trap to
take her out? That's totally
unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon! In the name
of the Moon, I'll punish you!
The five Sailor Guardians.
Those girls and the mysterious
Tuxedo Mask are such meddlesome
pests.
But now there are these two new
guardians who call themselves
Uranus and Neptune.
They present a bigger problem.
For like us, they are also
searching for the talismans.
Even worse, they keep showing
up every time we release a
Daimon on a new target.
The only explanation is that
they've figured out a way to
predict our movements.
Then we must use
their own ! tactic
against them, in
order to trap them!
Yes, Professor. I've got it.
Lure them in with a fake out,
then eliminate.
"To Save Our Friends: Moon and
Uranus Join Forces."
[Cheering]
Damn!
Did you see that?! Haruka beat
out everybody! Awesome!
Her racing skills
are top notch.
The best part is, she's
talented enough to hold her
own against all those pros
and still pull off a win.
Oh, no.
What is it?
What's wrong, Ami?
I got so excited I forgot one of
the new words I memorized.
[Groans]
[Grunts]
Here you go.
Thanks, Michiru.
Haruka! You were so amazing!
Bun‐head? You saw
the race?
You're all here?
Yeah! Mamo wanted to come so all
of us just tagged along!
Listen up, Haruka Tenoh, and
get this straight. Women have
no business racing bikes.
It shouldn't matter if the rider
is a man or a woman. Being the
fastest is what counts!
You talking back?
You're just jealous because
she's better than you!
You're all a pathetic bunch
of sore losers!
Say that again, turtleneck!
Knock it off!
Yamada!
Come on, guys, quit harassing
them. Walk away.
[Laughing] Better watch
your back, lady!
Let's go get a drink!
Mamo!
Who's he?
Katsutoshi Yamada. He came in
a very close second in today's
race.
He's extremely passionate about
Motocross racing.
But also believes in
a fair competition.
Ooh.
Just the exact type of person
who would have a pure heart
crystal.
Then we should definitely
keep an eye on him.
I'll take care of that.
All right.
Welcome, welcome, welcome one
and all! How do ya do there?
Come on over!
Our ever‐popular racer plushies
are on sale at rare discounts!
Get one right now before they're
sold out. Step right up, ladies
and gentlemen!
Oh how cute!
Comin' through. Let me see! Ah!
It's so soft!
[Grunts]
What? Hey, wait! Come back!
[Gasps] Usagi's out there!
Oh, you're right. I see her!
Nobody noticed that she
wasn't on the bus?
I certainly didn't. What now?
She's not a child. She can
catch another bus.
She always manages
to screw up!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Sighs]
I can't believe it!
They left without me!
Let's see. The next
bus is coming at...
[Screams] I have to wait an hour
for it to come!?
[Sighs]
Need a lift?
Oh, Haruka!
Hop on!
Um, but I...
C'mon. Don't be shy.
Okay then. Thanks
a lot, Haruka.
Hold on tight!
[Honking]
[Screams]
[Laughing]
He's doing this deliberately!
Hang on as tight as you
can, Bun‐head.
Okay!
Dammit!
Jeez! Was that truck driver
really trying to flatten us?!
That's just crazy!
I bet it's the guys
who threatened me earlier.
Oh no! They're here!
I knew it was them!
All right, where the hell did
she go?
[Gasps] I feel so safe. Almost
like when I'm with Mamo.
Hey, you smell really
nice, Haruka.
Is it rude of me to ask what
kind of perfume you are wearing?
Hey, quite!
Hmm? Huh!
You jerks looking for me?
It's her!
Let's get her!
[Gasps] Watch out!
[Screams]
[Groaning]
Quit trying to scare me off.
Listen, I won that race fair and
square, so just get over it!
Where's my inhaler?
Let's get out of here!
Wow that was
so cool!
I'll never quit! So help me, I'm
going to win the next motocross
race!
What the hell?
[Screams]
[Gasping]
I should have seen this coming.
That's odd.
Is something not
working?
Hmm.
It looks like my spark
plugs are fouled out.
The sea is raging. Hurry back
to the motocross practice track.
Got it. Something suddenly
came up.
My motorcycle won't run now, so
I can't give you a ride.
But if you follow that road, a
bus should come by soon.
Don't worry. I can
take care of myself.
Sorry!
I wonder what that was all
about. Something's wrong, I have
to follow her.
[Grunting]
[Laughing]
[Gasping]
Hah!
Tiren!
[Screaming]
[Laughing]
I've got your pure heart
crystal. Your racing days are
over!
Sorry, but I'll be taking
that crystal.
Hmm? Say what? Who are you?
Allow me to introduce myself.
Answering the call from a new
era, Sailor Neptune, here to
fight with elegance.
Deep Submerge!
[Screams]
There's no talisman in this
pure heart crystal.
You'll be alright. But you
need to get out of here, now!
[Laughing]
I've been waiting for you,
Sailor Neptune!
[Gasps]
Oh, I'm not here to get that
young man's pure‐heart crystal.
Im here to get you. And you just
fell right into my trap!
What did you say?
Double Tiren!
Ha!
Hmph!
[Laughing]
Spin! Spin! Double Spin! Spin!
Spin! Hah!
Die! Die!
Hold it!
Huh?
You're here too, Sailor Uranus?
How convenient! You can both die
together!
[Heavy Breathing] Haruka is so
fast! I'll never catch up!
[Gasps]
Hmph.
Tiren!
Huh!
Hmph!
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
Spin!
Hmph!
If you continue to resist,
your friend is going to die
a lot sooner.
Huh?
[Laughing]
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Huh?
Two against one.
That's not fair!
And who are you?
[Gasps]
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon!
I'm not taking sides...
... but I believe fights
should be fair and square,
with none of the dirty
tricks that you're pulling.
That's unforgivable!
So now, in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
Enough of this! Double Tiren!
[Screaming]
Uranus! Hurry up and get Sailor
Neptune out of here!
I never asked for your help!
Spin!
Behind you!
[Screams]
You okay?
I'm going to go after them! Out
of my way!
That's crazy! You're hurt and
it's way too dangerous!
Hmph.
Those two Sailor Guardians
have no teamwork whatsoever.
We should take advantage
of this and crush them.
Chain Ring!
[Gasps]
Oh no!
Tiren!
[Screams]
Doesn't look like you're very
well coordinated.
Watching the two of you is like
watching a three‐legged race
gone bad. [Laughing]
Spin! Spin! Double Spin!
[Grunts]
Don't you really hate it when
someone does the opposite of
what you want them to do?
How ironic that you'll be dying
together with someone you just
can't stand. [Laughing]
Spin!
[Gasping]
Uranus! Run away now! You must
live on to carry out our
mission!
Come on!
[Screams]
[Laughing]
[Gasps] Neptune!
[Screams]
Oh no!
[Screams] Hey!
What are you doing? The
waterfall's in the other
direction!
Hunt them down!
Don't let them get away!
Hmph!
Tiren!
[Heavy Breathing]
Uranus! Neptune might still be
alive. Aren't you worried about
her? You're not going to
abandon your teammate are you?
I can't get it off!
Stop yanking my wrist.
That hurts!
Quit whining!
[Sighs] Looks like
they've gone.
Let's go find Neptune, now.
What's with you? Don't you
care if your friend dies?
If we go out like this,
we'll all die.
She's your partner! How
in the world can you
act so calm and collected?
You're heartless.
You know nothing about me!
Huh?
Neptune and I made
a promise to each other.
If something were ever to
happen to one of us, we
wouldn't let our emotions
cloud our judgement.
[Gasps]
The one who survived would
continue our mission to find
the talismans.
We both made that
decision freely.
But what could be so special
about the talismans
that you would go to that
extreme to find them?
That's really none
of your business!
Well, I think it is!
I don't want to have to watch
people have their Pure
Heart Crystals removed
and then suffer and die!
How can you just stand back and
be that cold‐hearted? How?!
Answer me!
You're so naive.
Huh?
The Silence is coming to this
world.
Something terrifying is going
to happen soon. We need to
collect the talismans to save
us from total destruction.
You think I want there to
be casualties? But if you
knew that had to happen to
save the whole world...
Tell me what would you do
different?
Neptune, where are you?
Did you die?
[Grunts]
Oh, sorry.
Your shoulder, it's bleeding!
You should have said something
before.
Never mind it.
I'm fine.
Let me clean it
up, will you?
[Grunts]
That's enough.
Hold on, you don't want
it to get infected.
It's all right.
Leave it alone.
Stop trying to tough it out and
let me do this, okay?
But why?
Because I want to help you,
whether you want me to or not.
That's the way I am.
You really are something.
Anyway, I have a favor
I need to ask you.
What is it?
I know your shoulder is hurtin,
but I just can't bear it!
This itch in the middle of my
back has been driving me crazy!
Could you just
scratch it for me?
[Sighs]
A little more to the left. Right
there. Ah! That's perfect!
You're not what
I expected.
Huh?
Sailor Moon. I used to think
you ! were just sort of
annoying, but ! now that we've
spent some time ! together...
Huh? What about spending
time together?
They're here!
[Gasps]
This perfume smells familiar.
Could she be?!
Spin!
[Screams]
We can't stay here any longer.
Let's go look for Neptune!
Spin!
They're out in the open again.
Kill them.
Spin! Spin! Spin! Tiren!
You missed us! We're
over here! [Screams]
They're in sync?! That
doesn't make any sense. Just
minutes ago they were moving
in opposite directions.
Chain Ring!
Hah!
You idiot Daimons! But how
were they able to coordinate
a move that requires
split‐second timing? Impossible!
[Grunts]
Looks like she's still alive.
Not for long!
No you don't!
Sailor Body Attack!
[Grunts]
Spin!
World Shaking!
[Screams]
Spin!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[Screaming]
Lovely!
I'll get you next time!
We did it
together! [Giggles]
Yeah.
Although I have a higher
regard for you now, I still
won't let anybody get in
the way of my mission.
Neptune!
Uranus, why did you take such
a big risk to save me?
Actually, she's the
one who saved you.
Sailor Moon?!
That stupid Yuichiro!
Are you crying, Rei?
He's such a jerk! He doesn't
give a thought to my feelings!
That's not true. Yuichiro
cares about you a
lot. I don't understand
why you don't see that.
But...
No buts. This isn't like
you, Rei. You need
to tell him how you
feel and then make up!
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"A Man's Kindness: Yuichiro
Heartbroken by Rei."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.