Great! Now we have to find
the Messiah?! And what's up
with the new enemy's
outfit?! It's just crazy! As
for you Chibi‐Usa, you seem
to be distracted lately. Did
you forget the reason why
you came here in the first
place? You really need to
stop playing around and start
focusing on your training,
or else...
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
I see you've awakened. And
how is our Messiah of
Silence feeling today?
My head feels very heavy.
Hurry, Professor,
and get me what I need
to revitalize myself.
Yes, I understand. You
wish me to steal a number
of perfect pure hearts
from the humans...
Then transform them into
life energy, for your
awakening.
"Who is the True Messiah?
Chaos of Light and Darkness"
I want you to pay
close attention. The
cormorant dives under
water to capture fish.
The bird stores its catch in
its throat. Using instinct
to its advantage.
This will be the model in
our future efforts to steal
pure hearts.
We'll begin by releasing a
Daimon near the target.
The Daimon will swallow
the pure heart...
...and then return
here to me.
Once it's in the lab,
I'll make it cough up
its precious catch.
It's an extremely safe
and reliable method of
acqui‐‐ Huh?
[angry growl] Mimete!
You seem to be distracted.
Do you find my lecture that
boring?
Uh! No!
How dare you bring these to
the workplace? I get that
you're a fan, but nothing
must come between you and
your assignment. Which begs
the question‐‐‐ Have
you found a target with a
pure heart yet?
Of course I have,
Professor!
In fact, after a lot
of research, I found a
person with an
exceptionally pure heart.
Really? Well, let's see what
you can do with that
information, Mimete.
Keep in mind that Sailor
Moon is not the real
Messiah.
The truth of the matter
is, when the time
comes, the Holy Grail
will select its master.
So you're saying, the
first thing we need to
accomplish here, is to awaken
our Messiah of Silence?
Yes, Mimete.
That's exactly right.
U... Estern!
I think that celebrities
must have hearts of
exceptional purity.
After all, they bring
dreams to life for the
rest of us! Their energy
is exactly what I need
to awaken our Messiah.
In the right hands, the Holy
Grail is a force of good.
Bottom line, it grants
limitless power to fill
the world with light,
and crush all evil.
However, If it should happen
to fall into the wrong
hands...
...the world will be overcome
by evil and descend into a
new dark age.
Obviously, what the future
holds would change for all
of us.
[fright gasp]
That's what those horrible
visions were trying to tell
me!
Setsuna, you came from the
future specifically to warn
us about this, didn't you?
Yes. And now, I
have to leave.
What?! But why?! I must go and
help both Sailor Uranus and
Sailor Neptune, in their ongoing
quest to find the Messiah.
Uh, but wait a minute!
[upset sigh]
Why does it have to be just
the three of them?
[disappointed sigh] I
don't know... I wish
she'd told us more.
I think you're out of luck.
It's frustrating, but I'm
sure she has her reasons.
Even so...
Well Usagi, it's too bad
that you aren't the Messiah.
Come on. There has to be a
way for us to find the
Messiah.
Alright, but where do we
even start to look?
Hey wait! I just thought of
something! Maybe we should
narrow our search to ghosts!
So far, there's no proof the
Messiah even lives on this
plane of existence! [laugh]
[growl]
Get a grip!
Hi, everybody!
Hey, isn't Puu here?
Setsuna left. She said
she had a lot of things
she needed to do.
Oh, that's too bad, I was
hoping we could go to the
park together.
Hey, don't look at me! I
don't have any time to be
doing that!
Oh, phooey! Why don't
you tell us which
park you wanted to
go visit, Chibi‐Usa.
The Juban Nature Park.
Really?! That sounds
great! I'd be happy to
take you there!
You would?!
Wait a minute... Hold on, now.
We were
discussing something
important, Minako.
Oh my! Usagi, you're
starting to sound a
lot like Ami!
Minako. What's going on
at that park today?
Uhh...
Spill it, Minako.
Uhh... Okay, alright
already, I'll confess!
You see, they're
shooting a Yosaku Eda
movie there today!
What?!
Yosaku Eda?! Awesome!
Listen, Chibi‐Usa,
I'll go with you!
Of course you will. He is
pretty handsome. As a matter
of fact, he reminds me of the
guy who broke my heart...
No kidding. Then don't you
want to see him in person?
It's a plan then! Don't you
wanna come, Rei?
Uh, well, now that you
mention it, I suppose I
could...
Come on, Ami, let's
all go see him!
But Usagi If we do that,
what about the Messiah?
Well, you never know about
these things. Maybe the
Messiah will be there,
watching over
the film shoot!
Why?
Well, because...
Uhh, call it... my
woman's intuition?
[giggle] Well, in
that case let's go!
Ami's lost it.
You can't be serious? It
might be fun to have a
little change of pace. Think
about it for a moment.
We can't just sit here
worrying all day long.
Right! And for all we know,
we might end up studying
more efficiently if we plunk
ourselves down in
the middle of nature!
Hey! I thought we were going
for a break from studying!
True... Alright! Destination
Juban Nature Park! Let's go!
[cheering]
Oh dear... [disgusted sigh]
Yosaku Eda's here today
shooting a movie called
'Akafuji Gunman'.
This is it, but where's
Yosaku? There he is!
Oh! He's so hot! Alright...
Before I remove your pure
heart and kill you, you have
to try these cakes I made!
Yosaku!
Hold it, missy! Why are you
trying to get near Yosaku?
He happens to be doing some
very important work.
And the fact of the matter
is, you look pretty
suspicious, especially
dressed in those
funny clothes. Well I
brought him a present!
I made him some of
my home‐baked cakes!
That's a new one! [snicker]
You don't know him very
well, do you? He hates
sweets!
[horrified cry] You're pathetic!
Even
ants wouldn't go
near those cakes!
Learn your lesson, and
stay away from Yosaku!
My cakes!
What's the matter?
Did you have a run‐in
with my fan club?
Uh! I guess I did!
They've been getting a
bit carried away, lately.
Did you make these for me?
From scratch.
That was extremely
thoughtful of you. I'd hate
to see these wasted.
[gasp]
Delicious.
Thanks a lot. Bye.
You're welcome to stay
and watch us shoot.
Wait a minute! Those girls
said he hates sweets!
[gasp] There can only be one
explanation: This is love!
I mean, it's so obvious!
Yosaku took one look at me
and fell deeply in love!
But my destiny is still
to kill him and steal
his pure heart! I'm
sorry, my darling!
Forget about me.
Stay away!
You're going off to fight
again, and you'll be leaving
me all alone!
It's driving me crazy! I
can't take it! Don't come
near me!
That's not true, I'd
never leave you!
Joe!
Oh... He's so good!
Yosaku...
I feel so sick about what
I'm going to do to you. Once
I steal your pure heart, this
movie will never get finished.
But your
final performance will
not be forgotten.
I pledge to keep your last
moments locked in my mind
for eternity!
Oh no! The hat Ikuko Mommy
bought for me! Somebody
catch it!
That hat's very important!
I need it back!
Huh? Oh!
Here.
Thanks so much!
You're pretty lucky. It
didn't land in the stream.
[groaning]
Are you okay?
This happens a lot.
Don't worry about me.
Are you sure?
It'll go away soon.
[struggling breaths]
I'm fine now.
I'm so glad!
Hey! Would you like
to play together?
Huh?
I'm Chibi Usa!
[happy laughter]
Well my name's Hotaru.
Alright, take five!
I want to at least get an
autograph before I kill him.
There he is!
[shocked gasp]
Should we be
doing this here?
I don't really care. I just
want to be with you.
Oh you...Yosaku, I thought
I was going to be your
one and only! How could
you betray me like this?!
Well, in that case...
Daimon, show yourself!
[gasps]
U Estern!
[nasty chuckle]
Sailor Moon Super!
U Estern!
Run!
I can't believe Yosaku chose
that woman over me! Fine,
then! U Estern, go after him
and take his pure heart!
Hi ‐‐ Yo! U Estern! U Estern!
U Estern! U Estern!
U Estern! Hi‐‐Yo!
[stunned gasp]
Help us, somebody!
What's going on?!
[nasty laughter]
I still owe you for what
you did to my cake!
U Estern, show these ladies
what I'm talking about!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
[screaming]
[nasty laughter]
[gasp] What should I do? I
can't transform with
Hotaru right here!
Yay! Mako made us lunch!
Has anybody seen Chibi‐Usa?
Where'd she run off to?
[panic screams]
I hope she didn't
cause that.
Maybe they're filming
an action scene.
Bang! Bang! Bang!
A Daimon...
On a horse?!
Everyone, let's transform!
Right!
Scene change! U Estern,
re‐focus and go take
Yosaku's pure heart!
Yipee‐kai‐ay!
Hold it right
there, partner!
You've disrupted the filming
of a movie made for the
public to enjoy! You're an
outlaw who chases innocent
people with a gun! Wyatt
Earp might forgive you...
...but we won't be
that generous!
In the name of the Moon...
...We'll punish you!
Oh, shut up! U Estern,
go get those girls!
U Estern!
Stand back! I'll
take care of this!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
U Estern! Bang! Bang!
[gasp]
It didn't work?!
This Daimon is different
from the previous ones!
[nasty laughter] U
Estern, go for it!
U Estern!
Yumi!
Damn you!
Did you see that?
She swallowed it!
Way to go, U Estern!
Let's head back to
the Professor now!
U Estern!
World Shaking!
Deep Submerge!
[scream]
What the hell‐‐‐ ?! Answering
the call from a new
era, Sailor Uranus, here
to fight with brilliance!
And Sailor Neptune, here
to fight with elegance!
Huh? What do
we have here.
U Estern! Go after those
kids and catch them!
[fright gasp]
U Estern!
Look out!
Chibi‐Usa!
U Estern!
[frightened gasps]
[nasty laugh]
Don't even think about
moving until we're far
away from here!
And I'm warning you, if you
so much as flinch before
then, there's no telling what
will happen to this child!
[nasty laughter]
Chibi‐Usa!
Dead Scream!
[startled gasp]
It's Puu!
Now, Sailor Moon! Use the
Holy Grail to transform!
Crisis Make Up!
U Estern!
Rainbow Moon Heartache!
Love‐ Lovely!
[crying]
You'll pay for this!
I promise you will!
Who was that girl, anyway?
Eudial's replacement,
I think...
Usagi!
I feel exhausted...
Chibi‐Usa...
Oh, there you are!
[fright gasp] Are you okay?!
Your knee! It's bleeding!
I'm so sorry. It's because
you tried to protect me.
Don't worry, it's just a
scrape. I'm fine!
Maybe I can make it better.
[gasp of amazement]
That was amazing!
Everybody in my class thinks
I'm some kind of freak and
they all stay away from me.
I guess it is kind of creepy
to see that I have a power
like this.
That's not true at all!
Huh?
It's wonderful! I mean it!
You really think so?
Yeah!
Thank you, Chibi‐‐‐
Oh no, Hotaru, what's
wrong?!
I'll be fine.
Hotaru! You need help!
Hold on! I'll find someone!
That was close! Why do
they still need pure
hearts when the Holy Grail
has already appeared?
Sailor Moon, we'll leave the
Holy Grail in your hands for
now.
Wait a minute! Why don't we
look for the Messiah
together?
We can't do that.
You see... we're not like you.
We'll look for the
Messiah ourselves.
But why don't you
want our help?!
Why are they letting
Pluto join?
By the way, where's
Chibi‐Usa?
She was here just
a minute ago.
Aw! Why can't she
stay in one place!
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Don't mention it‐‐‐ Uh?
It's my Dad.
Is that you, Hotaru?
I wondered what happened to
you. I noticed it was late
and I was getting worried.
I had a slight attack
while I was out.
Daddy, this is Chibi‐Usa. She
was kind enough to walk me
back here.
How thoughtful. Thanks
so much, Chibi‐Usa.
You're welcome.
Will we see each
other again?
Mm‐hm. Of course!
We're friends now!
You really mean it?
A new friend.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
Bye! See you soon!
I can't wait! Come over any time
you want to play! We'll be here!
Okay!
I sure miss my Daddy.
Goodnight, Daddy.
Sleep well, Hotaru.
[crazy laughter]
Hey, Luna! Did you hear
about Chibi‐Usa's new
friend?
You mean Hotaru? I
hear she's very cute.
She is. I actually just came
back from visiting her place
with Chibi‐Usa.
I thought you had a
study session today.
Let's talk about that later.
Anyway, you won't believe
what happened there!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'A House Filled
with Evil Presence: The
Beautiful Hotaru's Secret'.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.