Have you ever thought about
what makes a pure heart? To
me, a pure heart is
something that comes
from the love and
friendship you feel
towards others. It
gives me the strength
to overcome anything.
And remember, even if you
return to the future, our
hearts will always
stay connected!
Bye, Chibi‐Usa.
Please take care!
Oh! Look, Mamo, it's
a full moon tonight!
You're right.
So pretty...
Yes. It's the
perfect night to relax.
Mamo?
Hm?
Don't you think it's a...
...little bit chilly?
Yeah, now that
you mention it.
I'd love to have
you warm me up.
Mamo? Huh?
Excuse me?
Mm?
Where are you going?
You're cold, right?
Let's go back inside
so I can fix you
some hot cocoa.
[sigh]
What's wrong, Usako?
What are you upset about?
Oh brother. How can
you be so dense?
'A Guardian's Realization:
Strength Lies Within a
Pure Heart'.
The stars are so pretty...
[gasp]
[scream]
A letter?
It's from Mommy! 'Dear Small
Lady. Are you doing well?
I miss you.
Please come home.
Love, Mommy. P.S.
Daddy misses you, too!
[giggles]
Small Lady...
Daddy. Mommy...
Did you miss me?!
Usagi...
What's wrong?
What's that you're
holding on to?
Look...
Oh. Okay, then...
Chibi‐Usa, this is‐‐
Yeah...
A letter from the future?!
Mm‐hm. It was a
message from her mom.
Ah that's me, come to
think of it! [laughter]
I see. Did it still read
like a 5‐year old wrote it?
Minako!
Give her a break. This
isn't the time for jokes.
Sorry!
What did the
letter say, exactly?
Well, it said
to come on home.
Alright and what
did Chibi‐Usa say?
Not much...
It doesn't have
to be right away.
I can go back there when
I feel like going back.
Well, kids her age usually
want to be around their
parents, right?
I'm sure she
wants to see them.
I have to agree.
Maybe she's having a hard
time admitting that she
wants to go home.
She does have a habit
of keeping her true
feelings to herself.
Well, I think now's a good
time for her to return.
Yeah, the crisis is over, so
we should let Chibi‐Usa
reunite her
with her parents.
Why don't we do
something special for her
before she goes home.
Good idea.
Any suggestions?
Oh! What do you
think about throwing
her a farewell party?
Hey! That's a perfect
way to say goodbye!
That's a great idea!
We'd better start
preparing for it.
Good! I'll be in charge
of planning the menu!
Where do you think
we should have it?
How 'bout Mamoru's place?
Would you ask him, Usagi?
Sure.
A farewell party?
Yep! We're doing it at
Mamo's place tomorrow.
Everyone's going
to be there.
But I haven't decided if I
want to leave right away.
We talked it over and we
want to do this for you.
There's gonna be tons of
food and drinks! It'll be a
great party, and
you'll have lots of fun!
So that's it? You want
me to leave that much?
Huh?
Nothing! Forget it!
Chibi‐Usa!
That's strange. Did you see her
face? She didn't seem too happy.
Yeah.
Stupid Usagi!
Doesn't she realize that
going back to the future
means I won't be
able to see her,
or Mamo, or any of the
others, ever again?!
They don't know how
much I would miss them.
[sobs] I don't want
to say goodbye yet.
[sniffles]
I don't want to go home!
I'm staying here!
What are you doing, Usagi?
I know from the way you've
been talking, that you want
to give Chibi‐Usa a
goodbye present, but
haven't you already spent
all of your allowance?
No problem. I wasn't really
planning on buying her
anything, anyway.
This has to be an
extra‐special present
that's worth more
than money. Oh!
I found it!
This will be perfect! I
absolutely loved this little
dress when I was her age!
Hm?
Chibi‐Usa?
Hi Mamo...
What's wrong?
Uhh...
[sigh] Well, I can't help
you unless you tell me.
Why don't you
come on in?
'Kay.
So, Mamo? Did I do something
wrong to make everyone hate me?
Hate you? Why do
you think that?
Everyone's suddenly talking
about a farewell party.
It's like they want me to
leave as soon as possible.
You've got it all wrong.
Everyone wishes you
could stay here forever.
We just want what's best for
you. And right now, that's
for you to be with your mom
and dad, who are waiting for
you back home in the future.
When you think about
it, I'm sure you miss
them too, don't you?
Usako and the others
do wish you could stay,
but they know in their
hearts that you can't.
I guess you're right...
Mamo...
Will you miss me?!
Of course I will. What
kind of question is that?
Oh, Mamo!
[sobbing]
Oww!
Usagi?
[gasp]
What are you doing?
Who, me? Nothing, really!
It's late. You
should be asleep.
But...
Goodnight.
I'm sorry, Chibi‐Usa.
[groan]
Stupid Usagi!
You don't understand
how I feel at all!
We hope you have
the best of luck in
your future, Chibi‐Usa!
Eat all you want,
there's plenty!
Okay...
Cheer up, Chibi‐Usa.
The future may be
farther away than a
distant tropical island.
But it's a whole lot closer
than heaven, so you can
come back and visit
us any time you want!
Heaven, really? Have you
visited there recently?
No...
Don't encourage
her, Minako.
Now let's get
this party rolling!
I know just the perfect
song to kick things off.
‐[cheering] Yay!
‐Now you're talkin'!
Renji!
Pure hearts...
Must gather pure hearts.
Sailor Moon Super!
Chibi‐Usa, we couldn't throw
you a party without bringing
presents! Why don't
you go first, Mako!
Hey, Chibi‐Usa. Here...
It's a special dish.
All you have to do
is heat it in your
future microwave,
then enjoy it with
your mom and dad.
Thanks so much, Mako.
My present for you is
a program I wrote.
Don't tell me your
going‐away gift is
another study aid?
That's not what it is, but
it is important to study
when you're young. When
you're tired
of all that studying, though.
Try this little game.
I wrote it myself,
it's super fun and
we're all in it.
That's very
nice. Thanks, Ami.
My present is a cassette
tape of my songs. I'm sure
you've already heard me
sing most of them before.
But the last one is a new
song I wrote just for you,
Chibi‐Usa. I really
hope you like it.
Thanks so much, Rei.
I put together an album of
photos that we took since
you first came
here. Ta‐da!
These should bring back
a lot of happy memories!
It's a little heavy though.
Wow, thank you, Minako.
Chibi‐Usa...
Yes, Mamo?
In the language of flowers,
a red rosebud represents
'purity' and 'charm'.
It matches you perfectly.
That's so sweet.
Hey, Chibi‐Usa.
Do you want to put all
your gifts in here?
Did you make this?
Yeah, but I'm not sure
I did that good of job.
You made her a puppy
backpack! Nice work, Usagi,
it looks great!
Are you crazy! This
doesn't look anything
like a puppy, it's a bunny!
Oh. Sorry 'bout
that. Guess it sorta
looks like a bunny.
Don't play dumb! I think
you said that on purpose to
make fun of me! What's
your problem anyway?!
Cut it out! And get over
yourself! I thought the pack
looked like a puppy,
so I called it a puppy!
Can you please stop saying
'puppy' over and over again!
[growling] You're
driving me crazy!
Now you're yapping like a puppy!
Agh! Quit it
with the 'puppy'!
[anger grunt] I can
see you made that
thing together with these clumsy
hands of yours! Here!
Use this bandage so you
don't bleed on everything.
Thank you.
Let me put it on for you.
I'll put these things
in for you, Chibi‐Usa.
Okay.
Chibi‐Usa, it might not be
the prettiest, but Usagi
stayed up all night
sewing that for you.
Wow...
[gasp] Rei and Usagi always stay
friends, no matter what
they say to each other.
Well, that's what
best friends do.
I don't believe I've
ever had a friend I
felt that close to.
[sigh]
Here is fine.
Huh?Any further will
just make it harder.
Thank you, everybody.
I appreciate everything
you've done for me.
Don't mention it, and
have a safe trip back.
Be a good girl, and listen
to your mom and dad.
Give everyone in
the future our best.
Take care of yourself.
Don't forget us. Think
about us sometimes, okay?
[sigh]
Usagi...
Chibi‐Usa... [sniffles]
[sniffles] Good‐bye.
Wait!
Usagi!
Wait! Hold on!
Let's not interfere. They
need some time alone.
O Guardian of Time! Tear
apart the heavens and open
wide for me the Door
of Space and Time!
I summon thee by
your true name.
Omnipotent God of Time...
Father of the Guardian!
O Chronos! Guide
me on my journey!
Protect this traveler!
Grant me the
Path of Light!
Chibi‐Usa!
[gasp] Usagi!
What's wrong with
you? Stop crying!
You're on your way
home, and you're gonna
live happily ever
after with your parents.
You should be happy!
Look who's talking.
You're the one... [sniffles]
Crying like a baby.
That's ridiculous.
I'm not crying.
I told myself
beforehand, I would see
you off without tears.
[gasp]
Usagi...
Usagi, I don't
want to leave!
[gasp]
Be good to your
mom and dad!
I'll miss you!
Good‐bye, Usagi!
Usagi!
[gasp]
Come with me! Something
terrible's happened!
[gasp]
Seems there was one
more Death Busters' egg!
And that egg has
turned into a Daimon!
Pure hearts throughout the
city are being sucked up!
Where is this happening? Tennoz,
in the ruins of the
Mugen Academy!
[groan]
[scream]
Mommy! Mommy!
[groan]
Listen up! The
indiscriminate taking of
pure hearts is
absolutely unforgivable!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And we are the
Sailor Guardians!
And last but not
least, I am Tuxedo Mask!
And now, in name of the
Moon, we'll punish you!
[growl]I don't think she cares!
Pure hearts. Give
me your Pure hearts!
Burning Mandala!
[gasp] [scream]
Damn you! [attack yell]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Renji!
[scream]
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[growl]
[gasp] [screams]
[screams]
Give me your
pure hearts...
Oh no!
What do we do!
It's Crystal Tokyo...
Daddy... Mommy...
[scream]
[chuckle]
Pure hearts.
Give them to me.
[growl]
[screaming]
Give me your pure heart.
[scream]
Your pure heart!
If only I had the Holy
Grail, I could turn into
Super Sailor Moon
to defeat her!
Sailor Moon!
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
Chibi Moon!
Ahh! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Sailor Moon and everyone
else you see around here,
are my precious friends!
How dare you go after
their pure hearts!
It's unforgivable!
I am the Pretty Guardian
Trainee, who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name
of the future Moon,
I'll punish you!
[growls]
Look out!
Agh!
I think you're in over
your head this time.
[groaning]
The heart of a young girl
with compassion is more
powerful than anything...
You have threatened to harm
these beautiful young girls.
I, Tuxedo Mask,
cannot forgive you!
You must trust in
the strength of your
friendships, Sailor Moon.
Right!
Tuxedo Mask is right.
Even without the Holy
Grail, I can protect
everyone if I have
compassion in my heart!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
Lovely!
You did it, Sailor Moon!
You saved us, yet
again! Well done!
Now that I think about it,
perhaps the Holy Grail is
simply pure heart with
compassion for others.
Wow! What a sunrise!
Wait, why are you here?
You might as
well admit it‐‐‐
You're all helpless
without me!
Oh really? Okay, girls, let's
get her! [giggles]
Hey, it's Luna P!
She has a letter
in her mouth.
It's from Mommy again! 'Dear
Small Lady. Thank you so
much for the wonderful
gifts. Be a good girl and
don't make trouble for
Usagi while you're there.
Bye‐bye now!
P. S. Bring some
more gifts when you
return next time.'
That's from
Usagi, all right!
So there you have
it! Good to be back!
Dear diary: Last night, I
had a beautiful dream where
I wandered into a Crystal
Forest and met Pegasus.
Let's go, Chibi‐Usa! Today is a
total solar eclipse
which happens
only once in centuries!
What's that? I'm not really
sure, but I guess the sun's
going to totally
disappear!
[scream]
Scary!Next time on Sailor Moon
Supers: 'Meeting of
Destiny: The Night
Pegasus Dances'.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.