The Silence is closing in.
Quietly, but surely. Is the
world really going to
disappear? What's that?
Hooray! Now I don't have to
go to school anymore?! Are
you serious? I mean, that
sounds great, but this is no
time to celebrate! Stop
fooling around or else...
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
[gasp]
[scream]
Are you the Messiah?
[grunting] If so,
then please, help us!
[gasp]
See what I mean?
This becomes the multiple.
Ahh...
Understand?
Not at all...
That ominous dream is
becoming more vivid each
day. And that girl, who
is she supposed to be?
"The Messiah of Silence
Awakens? Stars of Destiny!"
Hey girls.
Chibi‐Usa!
What brings you around? Hey! I
thought I told you
not to come here!
We're busy right now!
Usagi, chill out.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to interrupt your
after‐school
study session...
But I wondered if
my kind and beautiful
mommy could help me.
Why are you calling me
mommy all of a sudden?
Here, check this out!
A new planetarium's
opening? Cool!
Sounds interesting. Were
you hoping to visit it,
Chibi‐Usa? Yeah! It's supposed
to be educational.
And it says DJ Thomas
Harris will be narrating
the planetarium
show this week!
I love him!
Pretty cool, huh? It's
nearby, so I thought I
could take Hotaru with me.
I see...
Good idea. Alright, I'm in! How
about if we all go
there tomorrow?
Yay! That would be great!
Haruka told us to stay away
from Hotaru. I wonder why
she and the others
are so wary of her.
It's like they know
something about her
and don't want
us to find out.
The enemy is continuing
to collect pure hearts.
I wonder if Hotaru
possesses one that's
especially pure, so
Haruka and the others
fear she might
become a target.
That could explain
their obsession with her.
Hotaru is very sweet.
[gasp]
No, it couldn't be.
Oh boy! I can't
wait until tomorrow!
By the way Usagi, can
you buy us the tickets?
Pretty please?
I'll make it up to
you by doing your
chores for a week!
All right...Usagi! That's so
nice of you! You totally sounded
like a responsible
parent just now.
Really? I did?
It's almost like your
Chibi‐Usa's Mom...
Oh wait, you
are her mom!
Mommy!
Take it easy, willya?! I haven't
even given birth to you yet!
I think it's great that
you're trying to be a good
parent to Chibi‐Usa.
I wish I had a
cute daughter of my
own to look after!
Then you can have this
one! Here, take her!
Oh, I can't do that!
You love her too much!
Hey, stop teasing me!
We all know it's true!
My dream about the
world being destroyed...
It's growing more vivid
with every passing night.
Which is why the sooner
we find the Messiah, the
better. That's
especially true if
they awaken the wielder of
the Holy Grail as the
Messiah of Silence.
Hotaru Tomoe, she has
mysterious powers.
We need to find out
what or who she is.
We know she's the daughter
of Souichi Tomoe, the one we
suspect as a member
of the Death Busters.
So there must be
a connection.
The girl's image isn't a
hundred percent, but it's
gradually becoming clearer.
I can see that she's
standing in the light
of the Holy Grail...
She's holding some sort of
long weapon in her hand.
Wait! That could be...
The Scythe of Silence.
Silence Glaive!
Are you sure about that?!
It isn't completely clear.
You don't think‐?
Are you saying the
Messiah of Silence
is the Guardian
of Destruction, the
one protected by the
planet of Ruin?
If that's actually true,
there might be nothing we
can do to stop her.
This world will
soon be destroyed.
No. Even if we accept that
the Guardian of Destruction
has been reincarnated...
If we can find a way to
strike before she awakens
we have a chance. We
can save the planet!
I refuse to give
up all hope!
You're right. We can't
afford to accept defeat.
The future of this
world's at stake!
Soon...
Very soon...
I will awaken from my
slumber. When that happens,
the Silence you have
been waiting for
will appear and begin
to engulf this planet.
It took us years, but
ultimately it has paid off,
having chosen you as
the Messiah of Silence.
No question. I am the
only one who can make
your wishes a reality.
But not yet. I still
need more energy.
You must go out there
and collect pure hearts
so I can awaken.
Make yourself useful.
Go out there and
bring me what I need.
Yes!
Welcome to the Countdown
Fifty, everybody!
I'm your host, Thomas
Harris! Let's get right
into this week'! Top
Ten! At number Ten, up
from number Thirty
last week, we have
the Chatty Kitty Cats!
Oh, Thomas! You're
so cute, I'll be
seeing you soon...
[giggle]
Are you ready? Then
'Let's Get It On'!
Hello...
Hi, Professor.
Yes, I'm right on it.
Tell me, how do you
feel about stars?
Oh, well, that's great!
Yes, you can count on me.
I'll come through this time.
I will. After all,
you're the only one I
can count on, Mimete.
Stars, she says...
'I recall a song
about a star‐man...'
'They used to play
it at the disco...'
'He's waiting in the sky.'
I think that's how it went.
[giddy laughter]
[conversations]
Tomoe! Hey, there
you are! Wait up!
Can I come over
to your house?
I wanna do our
homework together!
Hi, Hotaru!
Chibi‐Usa!
Good to see you! Were
you waiting for me?
Mm‐hm! See this?
A new planetarium just
opened up in town!
I thought you
might be interested.
Looks like fun.
Good! Then let's
get going!
Right now?
I'm just heading
home from school.
I have to ask my dad for
permission before I can go.
No way! By then, the show
will have started! Come on!
Yes, but...
Will you guys quit your
yapping over there!
Are you two
coming or not?
Just one sec!
Hotaru, stop worrying about
what your dad might say.
You need to
live a little!
That's all part
of growing up!
She's right! And if you go home
first, then you'll never
make it to the opening.
We don't want to impose,
but we'd love to have you!
I appreciate the
invitation, but...
Please, Hotaru? I'll go
with you afterward to
explain it all
to your father.
You'd do that?
Alright, then. You
can count me in!
Great! I'm so excited!
Well, now that it's
decided, we'd better hurry!
This constellation is known
as Andromeda. Andromeda was
a princess, the daughter
of King Cepheus and
Queen Cassiopeia. Legend
has it that Andromeda
offered herself as a
sacrifice to a sea monster,
who was threatening
her country.
But she was
saved by Perseus,
who killed the monster.
Most stars come with
some kind of back‐story
based on ancient
myths and legends.
The life these heroes
lived remains within
our hearts forever.
[gasp]
She's here, just
as we thought.
Yes, her target is
probably the narrator.
Look, Hotaru is here too.
But why are Usagi and
the others with her?
Actually, that might be to
our advantage. If things
work out, it will give us
a chance to find out who
Hotaru Tomoe really is.
[affirmative grunt]
Next on our top ten
constellations, Scorpius and
Orion. Legend has it that...
Thomas, my darling...
...giant scorpion to punish
Orion for his arrogance.
Very soon, you'll be mine!
[nasty chuckle]
Sailor Moon Super!
[gasp] Huh?
Is that Setsuna?
Setsuna, what are
you doing here?
Has the enemy
appeared again?
Or is it because of Hotaru?
Are you here to
keep an eye on her?
Just tell us. Is there
something we should worry
about? There has to be
a reason you're here.
Isn't it time for you
to trust us and tell
us what's going on?
You're right. I've come to
the conclusion that, under
the circumstances, we
can't keep fighting
without telling
you the truth.
Uranus, Neptune, and I are
here for only one reason.
We've all come to stop
the encroaching Silence.
The enemy is called
the Death Busters, they
are invaders from
another dimension.
The Death Busters?!
Can you explain? What is
this 'Silence' you mentioned?
The destruction
of your world.
Sailor Mars, you've
already seen them in your
premonitions, haven't you?
[gasp]
Is that true? Come on, Rei...
Tell us!
I didn't mean to
keep it a secret.
Around the time those Daimon
monsters began appearing. I
started having frightening
nightmares, over and over again.
What you were observing was
the Silence, the destruction
of the world, which we
must try to prevent.
The destruction
of the world?!
Are you sure about this?
Allow me to show you. Try
to focus your minds on the
light from the orb at
the end of this rod.
As you concentrate,
you will be able to
see what Mars saw.
Oh no!
This is horrible!
[gasp] What is this?!
Is this the Silence
we're seeing?!
If the enemy's Messiah
of Silence awakens...
What you see here will
soon become reality.
Who's the Messiah
of Silence?
She is the final Guardian,
the one who must not be
allowed to awaken.
She will appear at the
moment the world is
about to be destroyed
and lead us all to
death and nothingness.
[gasp]
This Messiah of Silence...
Who is exactly is she?
Don't worry about that.
She will show her
true self very soon.
[gasp]
[fright screams and shouts]
[scared chatter]
[screechy laughter]
I'm U Choten!
And I'm here to help
you wish upon a star!
Hah!
[fright yell]
Time to make
a wish. Ready?!
Everyone! Take cover!
[chuckles]
Agh! No! Stay away!
Good work, U Choten!
[laugh]
Yes, it certainly
was! I rock.
[sigh] U Choten, don't worry
about the audience.
I'll take care
of them. I want you to take
Mr. Harris' pure heart.
U Choten!
But before she does...
Can I have your autograph?
[angry scream]
Guess not...
Fine! Who needs a
stupid autograph!
Charm Buster!
[screams]
Don't make a sound.
Let's hide here.
Okay...
Oh no! Hotaru!
I'll be okay. It's
just the usual attack.
It'll be over soon.
That means you have to go
to the hospital! Hang on!
I gotta transform...
Not yet.
Uranus! Hold on, and let's
see what happens.
I'm not sure we
have the time!
Hold it right
there, Daimon!
A planetarium's a
place for dreams!
A place where stars
shine bright!
A place of magical
discovery!
Anyone who ruins this
dream‐filled place...
Will have to deal with
the Sailor Guardians!
And now, in the name of the
Moon, we'll punish you!
Well, I guess nothing we
could have said was
going to keep those
girls from transforming.
Right. Why do you girls always
have to get in my way?!
U Choten!
What?!That pure heart
can wait a moment.
Get rid of these
Sailor Clowns first!
Fine!
Don't disappoint me now.
Yes, ma'am!
Are you all ready
to have some fun?
[affirmative grunt]
Well, here we go!
Wish upon a star!
[screams]
That's it! Keep wishing!
[yells]
[nasty laugh] U Choten!
Cast your eyes up
to the night sky!
Hotaru, hang in there!
This isn't good.
We're cornered here.
We have to do something!
Not heavenly enough for
you? Alright, then‐‐‐
[scream of pain]
What the‐?
That's as far as you go,
Daimon. No evil star shall
harm the innocent,
under my watch!
Your glow is about to fade!
[chuckles]You're wrong, my glow
is stronger than you think!
It's time!
Make a wish!
Ready?
Hah!
Stay clear, everyone!
Did Tuxedo Mask just
make things much worse?
Venus, get down!
Hotaru! You have
to stay down!
[gasp]
[gasp] It's her!
Hotaru?
What's...
...Going on?!
That symbol!
So Hotaru is...
A Sailor Guardian?
What's she doing?
Agh! What?
What's happening?!
I can't move!
Sailor Moon,
now's your chance!
Crisis Make Up!
Rainbow Moon Heartache!
[gasp] [scream]
Love Lovely!
World Shaking!
[gasp]
Deep Submerge!
Dead Scream!
[gasp]
No!
Look out!
[grunting]
Oh no, Sailor Moon!
Why'd you do that?!
Get away from that girl!
Why?Because Hotaru Tomoe is
the reincarnation of Sailor
Saturn! The final
Guardian of Destruction!
The fact is, when Sailor
Saturn awakens...
The world as we know
it, will come to an end!
So, move! You have absolutely no
idea how frightening
the Silence will be!
Unless we're able
to kill that girl,
Saturn will awaken!
And if that happens,
it will mean the end of
life as you know it!
We understand,
but we can't let you
kill this girl!
Listen to us! Even if
Hotaru is the Guardian of
Destruction, that doesn't
give you the right to
kill her! She's still
just a little girl!
What you're talking about
doing is horrible and cruel!
There has to be another way!
We thought that's what
you'd say, because
you care for her. But...
But there's just no other
way to save the world.
As upsetting as it might be,
we simply cannot allow
Sailor Saturn to awaken!
Unfortunately, that
is Hotaru's destiny.
What's going on?!
[gasp]
Hotaru!
What happened to her?!
Damn it!
[chuckle]
You had us worried...
What a bad girl, to go off
on your own like that.
Yes, that is
correct Pharaoh 90.
Indeed. That girl
is Sailor Saturn.
She is the Guardian
of Destruction.
And in this universe, I
believe there is no one
more perfect to be the
Messiah of Silence...
[laughter]
Hotaru's gone missing and
there's no‐one at her house!
Usako! Let's check
the Mugen Academy!
The school where Haruka
and Michiru go to?
We might find a clue there.
They say Hotaru is the
Guardian of Destruction,
but I'll never let
them kill her! I'm
going to find a
way to save her, no
matter what it takes!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'An Invasion From
Another Dimension: The
Mystery of Mugen Academy'!
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.