It's always fun rolling the
dice, and playing board
games or card games with
your friends, but things
can get out of hand
when winning becomes
the only objective. And gambling
with cheaters who
are willing to do
anything to win
is going too far!
I'm talking about
you, Daimon!
How dare you
endanger my friends!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
This one.
[sigh]
I did it! I won!
I guess I'm just a
magnet for bad luck,
even in card games.
The story of my
life. I'll never win
an ace of hearts!
Hey! Stop being so negative.
Losing once or twice in a
game doesn't mean anything!
All right, we'll play
concentration next!
I know you're really
good at that game!
[chuckle]
"Battle Inside the
Demonic Space; The
Sailor Guardians' Gamble"
All set. Now we will have a
Daimon that is capable of
winning against all odds.
[laugh]
Oh! It's already
three o'clock?!
Sir, why don't we
take a little break?
Ah, that reminds me.
Our kitchen is
totally out of snacks.
Sure is! Let me check the coupon
drawer then I'll go shopping.
Don't rush yourself
on my account!
Honestly, the Professor is
so naive. If he wants this
Daimon to be super strong,
he needs to go all out!
Besides, I'm the one who's
gonna be held responsible if
we fail. The stakes are
high, so I wanna make
sure our Daimon
is loaded to win!
[gasp] This might
not be a good sign.
[screaming]
I'm out of here!
What's that?!
[gasp]
[sigh of relief]
Are you all right,
Chibi‐Usa?
Yeah...
Thank goodness.
Huh?!
Wha‐?
[gasp]
What's going on?!
Hotaru! Hotaru!
[roar]
Oh my! Why do I
get the feeling we're
not in Tokyo anymore...
Be right back!
Uh, Usagi! I
need your help!
Wha‐? Chibi‐Usa?
What's wrong?
I'm over at
Hotaru's house.
Something really
strange is going on!
[scream]
Hotaru, what happened?!
What was that all about?
We better go over
there and check it out.
Mm‐hm.
What is it?
This drawer,
in my dresser...
It's got water and fish
swimming around.
Huh?! Wait, so
what happens
if I open this
desk over here?
[roar]
[scream]
[growl]
[gasp]
Whadda we do?
Don't worry, Hotaru...
Help is coming, but
until it gets here, we
need to hang tight. Okay?
Okay...
That took longer than I
thought. So hard to find a
good gluten‐free
snack these days.
C'mon. Open up!
What is this, some
kind of prank?
Open up, you idiots! I'm
the master of this house!
Fine! No snacks
for anyone!
I'm gonna break
down this door!
This is Hotaru's house.
Are you picking up any
strange readings? Yes.
The entire house somehow
got connected to
multiple dimensions.
It's very unstable
and dangerous!
Huh?
[gasp] What's this?
Is it possible that they
figured out who I really am?
It's okay sir, we're here to
help rescue your daughter.
In case you didn't know,
we're the good guys!
We're the Pretty
Guardians who fight
for love and for justice!
And in the name of the
Moon, we'll punish you!
[growling]
You moron! Superheroes
aren't supposed to threaten
the person they've
come to help!
Hey, that hurt! There was no
need to slap me like that!
Well, it was your fault for
saying such a stupid thing!
Looks like I was
just being paranoid.
Is my daughter in danger?
Yeah, but just leave
everything to us!
C'mon. We need to
hurry, Sailor Moon.
Huh? In one hour, this house
will be sucked into a stronger
dimensional riff and
be completely destroyed!
Yikes! This is more
serious than I thought.
It's so hot.
I need water.
[gasp]
Now it's freezing! This
doesn't make any sense!
Okay! Do your thing,
Sailor Jupiter!
Wait a second!
Huh? What are you preparing
to do, Sailor Moon?
Open the door. First I'll
have Jupiter try her
Sparkling Wide Pressure,
and if that doesn't work
Mars can use her Burning
Mandala to make the
door disintegrate.
[sigh]
What do you plan on doing
while we do all the
work?[chuckle] I thought I'd
watch and cheer you on.
I'm good at that.
Plus it's fun.
Are you sure I can count
on you girls to save my
daughter's life?
Of course you can.
Please ignore silly
blonde comrade.
The rest of us are really
quite competent.
You talkin' about me?
If you force
that door open from the outside,
it'll destroy the balance
of the current distortion
inside and the whole
house will be sucked
into another dimension. Are you
getting how risky your plan
sounds, Sailor Moon?
Or maybe we need to
draw you a picture?
Cut it out you two!
Hm? Clearly, We can only
open the front door
from inside the house.
Right. Um, how do we get
inside if we can't go
through the front door?
Duh! By using our
Sailor Teleport!
Oh yeah!
Good grief!
Right! Let's do it,
everybody. C'mon!
Yeah, yeah. We're coming.
Sailor Teleport!
[meow]
[grunt]
Huh?!
Hey guys, looks like
we teleported to
the wrong location.
No, we didn't.
We're actually inside
Hotaru's house.
Huh?!
How ironic. Of all the
people on this planet,
I'm relying on the
Sailor Guardians,
but I can't afford to
lose Hotaru now.
Ah! I completely forgot
about the food I bought.
I'll just have a little
snack while I wait.
Jeez! I don't understand.
How can this be
Hotaru's house?
When the shock wave
happened, many different
dimensions collided
and twisted together.
That's why we're
experiencing so many
sudden changes. But
at the same time
we're still inside
Hotaru's house!
[screams]
I sense that Chibi‐Usa
and Hotaru aren't
too far away from here.
I should've paid attention
is spatial physics.
It's already been
twenty minutes...
I hope everyone's okay.
Hey!
What's going on?
Anything new?
Hotaru Tomoe has
apparently become trapped
in another dimension.
Sailor Moon and the others
have gone after her, but
there's a very good chance
that none of them will
ever make it back here.
Quite frankly, that wouldn't
bother me one little bit.
Haruka!
I know it sounds harsh.
But it's better to get
rid of Hotaru Tomoe
while we can.
Before she becomes
a real threat.
Huh?
Where are the‐‐?
Chibi‐Usa...
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, uh‐huh! I just
need to move around!
I actually think it
would be safer if we
stayed in one place.
Nah! [laugh]
[screaming]
Chibi‐Usa!
[scream]
Hotaru!
Chibi‐Usa! [grunting]
Sailor Moon Super!
Hotaru! You're
gonna fall! Let go!
Let go!
We're about to shift
into the next dimension,
andthat's where we'll find
Chibi‐Usa and Hotaru.
Are you sure?
Without a doubt!
It's changing...
Three, two, one...
Huh?
[screaming]
[sigh]
[gasp] There they are!
Oh no!
[scream]
Venus Love Me Chain!
[gasps]
C'mon! Help me pull
them up, guys! Hurry!
I'm afraid we can't use the
Sailor Teleport here with
Chibi‐Usa and Hotaru.
It's far too dangerous.
[gasp] Then what
are we gonna do?
Would you be able
to save one of us?
Huh?
If you can only take one of
us, please take Chibi‐Usa.
I don't mind if I
have to stay here.
Hotaru!
It's better this way. I'm a
freak who brings bad luck to
everyone around me. I really
don't deserve to live.
I'm begging you guys!
Please, just save Chibi‐Usa!
Listen to me...
Huh? Everything is going to be
all right. We'll find a way
to save both of you.
Besides, you're Chibi‐Usa's
very best friend!
It would break her heart to
hear you talking about
yourself like that.
Sailor Mercury is super
smart. She'll figure out a
way to get all of us back.
Any dear friend of
Chibi‐Usa's automatically
becomes our friend too.
We'll get out of
this place together.
Okay.
They only have half
an hour left...
I think we're
near the exit!
[screams]
[grunts and groans]
Is everyone okay?
Just peachy...
This is really getting old.
So is this door the way out?
I think so. As far
as I can tell.
Well, I guess there's only
one way to find out.
Oh great.
[gasps]
Welcome, Sailor Guardians!
[screaming]
Glad you were able to make
it. I'm the Daimon who lives
all alone in this
strange dimension!
U'Ikasaman! Ready to play!
The distorted dimensional
energy in this house is
coming directly from her.
That's right! I hope you're
enjoying your adventure,
because it's not over.
So that means... We won't be
able to get out of this place
unless we defeat her!
Now hold on a second!
Huh?! Fighting is
not the answer.
Can't you see, I'm not
the violent villain type.
Well then, what type
of villain are you?
Isn't it obvious?
I love gambling.
If you can beat me in a game
of chance, I'll return you
to your normal world.
No deal! Burning...
A word of caution...
[gasp]If you're gearing up to
fight, I'll send you to
another strange place.
We'll play your games! But
if any one of us wins, you'd
better send us right
back to where we came
from, as promised!
Of course! Only, what
happens if I win? I think
you should have
to stay here and
play gambling games
with me for all eternity.
Let the chips fall
where they may!
Right! I'm ready
for your challenge!
I'll be your
first opponent!
You're on!
I pick red sixteen!
Hmph!
Agh!
You lose!
You cheated!
There! Now let's see
how well you do.
[chuckle]
[gasp]
You lose, as well!
And checkmate.
Looks like I won!
Oh, really? Look again.
Agh...
Guess your win
went up in smoke!
Next challenger.
We're double‐trouble!
Guess my mom was wrong
when she said video
games were useless!
Go!
[screaming]
Oops!
Ohh.. Guess I forgot to give
you instructions. When you
accelerate at my arcade,
cars tend to crash! [laugh]
No more challengers?
Guess that means I've won!
Not so fast!
Huh?
You haven't won yet.
We'll take you on!
Chibi‐Usa!
Okay, what game
do you wanna play?
How 'bout Old Maid?!
[gasp]
Fine with me!
Game on!
[grunt]
I wonder how they're
doing in there?
They only have
ten minutes left!
Now! Go ahead,
it's your turn.
Okay. Here I go.
This one...
[gasp] So easy. Her childish
delight shows me
that's not the one to take.
How about this one?
[chuckle]
Hm? The Joker?!
Huh?!
[laugh]
She fell for it!
Dammit! How dare
she trick me!
[scream] Oh, I was just waiting
for you to take that one!
Oh, really...
Wow. Glad I did.
[growling]
That trick always
fools everyone!
Where did I go wrong?!
And here!
I did it! I won!
Yay! Chibi‐Usa!
Now fulfill your promise.
Release us and send
us out of this place!
Not yet!
I'll only let you
out if this girl is
able to defeat me!
Me?!
If you don't like it,
nobody gets out!
You only have five
minutes, anyway.
Okay! Hotaru, take a good
look at her face before
you pick either card!
One is the Joker and the
other is the Ace of Hearts!
Oh, I never get this right!
I need to do whatever it
takes to make her pick the
Joker. Okay then...
You can watch my face all
you want, but not even I
know which one is the Joker.
So take your time
before you choose.
Huh?
This will decide
everyone's fate...
[chuckle] Sucker! I
marked the Joker earlier.
And she thinks I don't
know which is which...
All I have to do is confuse
this timid, little girl
and she'll pick whichever
card I want her to.
Oh! My heavens, you
really want that one?
[gasp] Uh...
Oh, yes.That might
be a better choice.
Hotaru!
Trust yourself. Choose
the one you feel best
about picking up!
Don't hesitate!
Be bold and flip it over!
It'll be all right!
You can do it!
We all believe in you, Hotaru!
Why would you?
Because we're your
friends, and that's what
friends do for each other.
Hotaru, just think of it as
a game of concentration.
Yeah!
Ah?!
[gasp]
Wow, you did it, Hotaru!
Chibi‐Usa, thank you!
[gasp] Hotaru!
Don't worry, she just
fainted from exhaustion.
Now, keep your promise!
Yeah! Let us out of here!
I don't remember
making such a promise!
What did you say?!
You dirty liar!
Yeah, so what? [laugh]
Agh! Unforgivable!
Moon Prism
Power Make Up!
Pink Sugar
Heart Attack!
Uh...
That's weird...
I even used extra energy...
[scream]
[screaming]
You could've killed
me with that thing!
But it set you free.
Oh look at that!
Crisis Make Up!
Rainbow Moon Heart Ache!
[screaming]
Love‐Lovely!
[sigh]
We're all back!
You did it, Sailor Moon!
Wake up, Hotaru!
Sailor Chibi Moon, wait!
Huh?
You can't let her see
you dressed like that.
You need to change back.
Oh, you're right.
Thank you for
saving us, Hotaru.
Hotaru! Oh,
thank goodness!
I can't thank you
people enough for
saving my daughter.
[crazy laugh] There will
come a day when you will
look back and regret
having saved her,
Sailor Guardians!
You don't seem
surprised that they're
back safely, Haruka.
She isn't. I'm sure Haruka
has a lot more faith in
Sailor Moon than she's
willing to admit to us.
Thanks, blabbermouth.
You came through for us,
Chibi‐Usa. You and Hotaru.
Mm‐Hm! Hotaru and I make
a pretty good team.
I think we're unstoppable!
I once read that a person's
destiny is predetermined.
That the star you were born
under will decide who you
are, and what you'll become.
Really? So I'm off the hook?
It's actually the fault of
the stars that I'm a clumsy
crybaby who did poorly on
her test yesterday? [laugh]
I don't think they can take
the fall for all that, Usagi.
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "The Messiah of
Silence Awakens?
Stars of Destiny."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.