Oh, Chibi‐Usa, is this your
new friend, Hotaru Tomoe?
She's so adorable and
delicate and polite‐
not like you at all!
You could learn a
thing or two from her!
Just make sure not to be
rude when you're visiting
her place, you got that?
And if you cause
her any trouble...
In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
[singing]
So you're in a good mood
today, Chibi‐Usa. What's up?
[chuckle] Well, as it just
so happens, I've got a new
friend.
Ah‐h! Tell me all about him.
Is he really
cute? What's the
color of his eyes?
Mehh!
I'm not telling you
anything, "Miss
nosey‐posey", so there! Ha!
[growling]
Ah!
[screaming]
[drowning groans]
Jeez! What's going on in
there, bubble heads?! Keep
it down, would ya!
"A House Filled with Evil
Presence: The Beautiful
Hotaru's Secret."
We've been waiting for you,
Mamoru. Or should I say
Prince Endymion...
I was only called that in
the past Silver Millennium.
How do you know that name?
We're Guardians of both
the past and future.
Uranus Planet
Power Make Up!
Neptune Planet
Pluto Planet
Power Make Up!
Protected by Uranus, Planet
of Wind, I am Sailor Uranus.
Protected by Neptune,
Planet of Seas, I am
Sailor Neptune.
Protected by Pluto,
Planet of the Underworld,
I am Sailor Pluto.
We are the three Guardians
of the Outer Solar System.
The Outer Solar System?
Mm‐hmm.
We were given powers far
greater than those of an
ordinary Sailor Guardian, to
insure that no invaders
break through.
In ancient times, our role
was to defend the Silver
Millennium from threats
coming from outside
the solar system.
[fighting grunts]
But by the time we awakened
in this era, the enemy had
already established a
strong foothold on this
planet in secret.
We feel responsible
that they got by us.
We should have been more
vigilant, and detected
what they were doing.
I assume you're talking
about our latest enemy,
the Death Busters.
Why don't you work with
Sailor Moon and the other
Guardians?
Talk to them
instead of me.
Those girls would
just get in our way.
What?!
This battle is far too
much for Sailor Moon
to undertake.
Same goes for the
other Guardians.
The fact is, the Death
Busters got here on
our watch.
They're our greatest
enemy and it's our
job to defeat them.
What? Chibi‐Usa came to
you for advice, as well?
Yup! She was going to visit
her friend's house for the
first time and she wanted to
know what she should wear.
You're planning to get
dressed up? I wouldn't
do that.
You should look nice,
but keep it casual.
If you dress up too much,
you can't have any fun.
Oh really? She wanted my
ideas about a present.
Hm. I really don't think you
have to bring anything.
But a book might
be a good idea.
That way you can talk about
the kind of books you're
both interested in.
She really wants to make
a good impression. She
must like him a lot.
It sounds like he goes
to a different school
and is very quiet.
She didn't say she
had a boy‐crush.
Hey, I just finished a fresh
batch of cookies. I'll wrap
some up for you to bring.
Had I known they were for a
boy she liked, I would have
shaped them all to look
like his face! Uh. Huh?
That sounds a bit extreme.
For a first date.
You just don't know
what she'll do.
Oh, shut up!
Chibi‐Usa came to me
for an opinion, too.
Okay...
What should you say when
you first arrive? Mm..
Hey! I've got an idea! I'll
go with you and tell you
exactly what words
you need to use.
Uh, well..
[angry growl] Usagi, you
have a study session here
all day today, remember?!
Look, there's MJ!
Huh? Where? Where?
Michael‐Michael?!
[scream] Michael...
She actually fell for that?
Unbelievable...
Don't you think it would
be better to give her a
book that has more serious
content? No, I just managed
to get the last copy of this
before it was sold out.
But I wanted Katakuri Ukon's
new manga for myself.
Sorry, no can do. Sure you
won't change your mind
about tagging along, Usagi?
[laugh] Not the
slightest chance..
I just want to know what
your new friend is like.
Very cute. But,
gets sick a lot.
Ah well, that's really
terrible, but on the other
hand, it is kind of romantic.
As your guardian, it's only
right that we should meet.
You're no guardian of mine.
Don't be silly.
Let's get a move‐on.
Quit pushing me!
O great Messiah of Silence,
the time of your awakening
is drawing near.
You do realize I will need
vast amounts of energy to
make that happen.
Of course and the best
source of energy comes
from pure hearts! I mean to
collect as many as possible
to enable you to awaken!
I trust that will be
to your liking...
Whoa! This is amazing!
What a huge place!
[struggling grunts]
Push it for me.
Huh? Okay, uh..
Oh, hello there..
Huh?
[gasp]
K‐Kaolinite!?
Usagi, you're
such a klutz!
Chibi‐Usa.. Look what you did.
You dropped the whole
bag of cookies.
May I help you girls?
What's going on? Do
we have visitors?
Apparently...
Oh, you must have
stopped by to see Hotaru.
Seriously?
Yeah!
Hello again. Welcome.
I'm Hotaru's dad.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
And let me introduce my
personal assistant, Kaori.
Do me a favor. Hotaru
is a bit busy right
now, so could
you show these
young ladies into
the drawing room?
[chuckling]
Of course. Let me brew up a pot
of my favorite coffee for them.
Right this way...
Thanks!
Guess I was wrong. She
looks like her, but
she isn't Kaolinite.
I mean, there's
no way she could
possibly be Kaolinite.
We saw her die
from that fall.
[humming]
[chuckle]
"What are you
doing here, Drop?"
"It's your fault
that Andre is dead."
"That's not what
happened, Aunty!"
"Yeah, that was‐"
"Shut up, get out!"
"Drop!"
[sobbing] That poor girl
really didn't deserve this.
Hello, this is Mimete..
Well, finally. Have you been
able to scope out a new
target for us, Mimete?
Huh? Ah‐ah‐ah‐oo.
Of course I did! I have my
eye on someone right now!
He's pure‐hearted
and quite talented.
He'll do fine.
I'm going to get his
autograph. I mean, he's
appearing at the Juban
Bookstore today for an
autograph‐ signing session.
Perfect. I'm going to whip
up a Daimon for you to take
along so you can get more
than just an autograph.
[laughing]
Looks like my special
brew is ready now!
[crazy laughter]
U Henshu!
Sailor Moon Super!
[street chatter]
Done. Here you go.
[scream of delight]
Thank you so much!
My pleasure,
little darlin'.
I'll treasure this always,
even long after you're gone.
[clock ringing]
We still don't
have our coffee.
Usagi...
[annoyed grunt]
Hotaru must be very busy.
[nervous breathing]
[surprised gasp]
[excited gasp]
Chibi‐Usa, hi!
Hotaru!
Uh, your friend's a girl?
I never said anything
about a boy.
[chuckling]
Your sister? Right?
She's just my cousin, Usagi.
She tagged along because she
thought I had a date
with some hot boy.
What?! I came along
to keep you company.
Hmph! That's not true.
Well, as your guardian,
it was important for me
to introduce myself.
That's a bunch of baloney.
You're only here because
you like to butt into
my business. Right?
You're such a liar! I'm
just making sure you're
not chasing after
yet another boy!
Ha! I'll have you know I'm
very popular with boys.
Unlike you I don't
have to chase them!
[giggling]
Look what you did! She
can't stop laughing at us!
Why is it my fault?
Sorry, but you're kind
of funny. I'm glad you
were able to come.
I'm Hotaru Tomoe.
Uh! Yeah. I know. Thank you
for having both of us over.
Sorry I kept you waiting
in here. Why don't we
all go to my room?
[gasp]I guess I'd better take
the coffee up there
now... Is that right?
No! I'll take care
of it, thank you!
And stay out of my
personal life.
[chuckle]
Sorry about that. She's just
my Dad's assistant and often
comes here to help with
his research.
He's a scientist.
And where's your
mother, Hotaru?
She died a while back...
Uh...
Oh, I'm so
sorry... Really.
Oh, it's all right.
Anyway, I wanna
hear about you.
Ah!
Wow!
It's just soo pretty...
It's like another
world. It's wonderful!
Thank you.
Ah...
Hotaru!
What's the matter? What
happened? Are you okay?
Hotaru!
I'm‐ I'm fine.
I got a little dizzy for a
moment. I'm really all
right. It was nothing.
[relieved sigh]
What is this?
Um, it's just a brooch.
What a mysterious brooch..
Just touching it makes
me feel so much better...
Like it's giving me
unlimited power...
Hotaru?
Did I say
something just now?
Uh...
I did, didn't I?
Did I offend you?
No, not at all!
Hey, why don't we give
Hotaru her presents now?
Good idea. I hope you like
it. Picked it out myself.
Ta‐da!
What's that?
An autograph session
with Katakuri Ukon...
[scream]
[shriek] It's just
about over!
Why didn't you notice
this when you were at
the bookstore?!
You were there, too! You
should have noticed it!
It's your fault!
Not!
Great turn out. Congrats!
Can't wait to read the book!
Bye now!
Mr. Ukon!
Mm?
Oh, it's you.
Just wanted to say thank you
for your autograph earlier.
Oh, my pleasure...
However, there's just one
more thing I want from you.
It's actually for my boss.
Wha?
Your pure‐heart crystal.
Daimon! Show yourself!
What is that?
U. Henshu!
You need to meet your
deadline... and I'll help!
[growling]
Hope we're
not too late!
Hurry up!
You kinda scared us.
Sorry...
We're friends. No need
to apologize to friends.
[fear scream]
What's wrong, Usagi?
[growl]
Agh!
Go take Hotaru
somewhere safe!
'Kay! Be careful.
Change of plans, Hotaru!
Huh?The autograph session's
over. So let's go to
the arcade!
Moon Cosmic
Power Make Up!
[growling]
Hold it right there!
Huh? There are still people who
haven't received autographs!
How dare you gobble up
their chance to have one!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
You again?! You're not gonna
make me cry this time!
U Henshu, get her!
As you wish,
Editor‐in‐Chief!
I'm not your editor! Just
hurry and slice her up!
Yes, ma'am!
Special Attack! Blank
Drafts of Hell!
[gasp]
[scared screams]
And here's your
cover page!
[gasp]
[struggling grunts]
Can't move...
[nasty chuckle]
Cut and paste!
Snip, snip!
Huh?!
What exactly are you
gonna do with those?
Cut and paste your
heart's delight!
No‐o!
Dead Scream!
[scream]
[surprise gasp]
Pluto!
Leave this battle to
us, Sailor Moon.
Uranus! Neptune!
Thank you.
Hurry up and get
away from here.
Huh?
Hey! You can't just
show up uninvited!
Deep...
...Submerge!
[laugh] I read the
weather report!
You heard me. Now go!
But why? G‐pen, mapping
pen, kabura pen!
[attack yell]
But, Uranus! Why can't
we fight together?
We're all Sailo‐
You're in the way!
Completed drafts of hell!
World...
Shaking!
Scrounging up enough
strength to meet the
deadline!
Right on time!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[screaming] Sailor Venus!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Mercury!
The Sailor Guardians
are here!
Why are there so
many of you?!
Yes!
Outer Guardians...
Tuxedo Mask!
You say you want to work
alone, but sometimes it
takes the power of everyone.
Sailor Moon and her friends
are here to help, and it
seems like you need them.
What? Nine against
two? That's so unfair!
What should we do?
Obviously, you get
rid of them all!
They're so many. How
am I going to do that?
You've got that amazing
weapon, so work it!
But, it's all used up.
So are you!
You're useless!
Go for it, Sailor Moon.
Okay.
Crisis Make Up!
Rainbow...
Moon Heartache!
Uh...
Gotta go, nice
knowing ya!
Huh? What? Wait! Agh!
End of story!
Thanks, everybody!
I was kind of reluctant to
help someone who would skip
out on her study session.
[I'm sorry...
Where'd Chibi‐Usa go off to?
We should give her a call.
She's probably worried.
You went to Game
Center Crown, huh?
Yeah, and she had a lot of
fun! She had never been to
an arcade before.
Can you believe it?
And you must have had a lot
of fun, 'cause you've
completely forgotten
that I was getting
my butt kicked!
[chuckle] Hotaru's
situation at home is
complicated, but she
seems like a good kid.
Yeah. I hope I get to
see her a lot more.
I like her!
Yay! I, Minako Aino, am the
Pretty Guardian Teen Idol
that's going to take
the world by storm!
That's so awesome, Minako!
I'm great at sports! And I
look amazing in a swimsuit!
Everybody will fall for me!
Uh hey, Minako? Oh,
Usagi, don't bother me
now. I'll give you
my autograph later.
Okay, but I just wanted to
let you know your swimsuit
has a tear in it!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "I Love Idols:
Mimete's Dilemma."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.