Oh no, Hotaru's gone
missing! And Chibi‐Usa says
her house is
empty, as well!
Haruka and the others aren't
the least bit concerned.
They say she's the Guardian
of Destruction, and they're
determined to eliminate
her. But she's our friend,
and I won't allow
them to hurt her!
In the name of the
Moon, I will save her!
An Invasion From Another
Dimension: The Mystery of
Mugen Academy.
Move! You don't
know how frightening
the Silence really is!
Unless we can kill
that girl, Sailor
Saturn will awaken!
If Saturn does
awaken, it will mean
the end of this planet.
[groaning]
Chibi‐Usa!
[gasp]
[crying]
Small Lady...
Puu...
You have to tell
me right now!
Where did you
take Hotaru?!
By the time I arrived
there was nobody here.
You're lying! Hotaru is my
friend and I know she
wouldn't just go away
without telling me!
Puu, this is all your fault.
Hotaru's gone because
of the mean things
you said about her!
You scared her away
and now I don't know
if I'll ever see her
again! [crying]
Don't cry, Small Lady...
But she's gone!
It's your fault!
I hate you!
I understand...
There was no one at Hotaru's
house when we went by.
Professor Tomoe wasn't
there, nor was his
assistant, Kaori.
End result? We're left
without a single clue.
Are you finding anything on
the computer, Mamo?
If there's any information
on Professor Tomoe, it
should be in the scientific
society's files.
I'm checking those, first.
There! Souichi Tomoe...
It says here he's a
leading genetic engineer.
And a professor
at Mugen Academy.
Mugen Academy?
Haruka and Michiru go there.
So does Hotaru.
Wait a minute, I've
heard of that place, too.
Isn't it a special
school for the gifted?
Yes, I hear they have a
unified curriculum from
primary school
through college.
And the campus is
in a skyscraper, with
all the latest equipment.
Huh?
What is it? Souichi Tomoe isn't
just a professor...
He's also the owner
of Mugen Academy.
Ohh...
Owner? As in, it
belongs to him?
You think that's
where they went?
We can't be sure, but it's
possible it holds a clue.
In that case, we should
really check it out.
[gasp] Setsuna!
Chibi‐Usa!
What happened to
you? You know better
than to go out
at this hour!
Wait, you‐‐? Look at
you, you're sopping wet!
What were you
doing out there?
Didn't you bring
an umbrella?
You're going to catch a
cold in those dripping wet
clothes. Come with me,
we're going to get
you changed
immediately!
Usako!
But Mamo...
Thank you for
bringing her back here.
You're welcome.
I'll go now.
Hold on a minute.
I wanted to ask some
questions about Mugen
Academy. You mind?
From what I know, Mugen
Academy was established
three years ago,
by Souichi Tomoe.
Within a short period
of time, many bizarre
incidents began
to occur there.
Uranus and Neptune became
suspicious, and entered the
school as students, in
order to investigate.
They went undercover?
Were they able
to find anything?
They think Tomoe
maybe connected
to the Death Busters?
Wait. Are you saying
that Hotaru is...
...involved with the
Death Busters, as well?
We don't know.
The one thing we are
sure of, is that Hotaru
Tomoe appears to be
the reincarnation
of Sailor Saturn.
That doesn't matter!
I know that Hotaru's
not our enemy.
Chibi‐Usa... I
don't care who you
think Hotaru is!
She's my friend!
She's good! And I
won't let you hurt her!
If you do, I'll
never forgive you!
Setsuna...
Even if Saturn is the
Guardian of Destruction
isn't she still a
Sailor Guardian?
There has to be some
other way to save this
world, without having
to take her life?
There isn't, and that's the
bottom line as to why we
didn't want any of you
involved in this battle.
What is it?
Professor, this is Mimete...
I believe I've located our
next target. He's studies
subspace physics,
Professor Sergei Asimov.
And he's accessible,
he'll be speaking
today at Mugen Academy.
Yes, I know. It's
about 'The Theory of
Alternate Dimensions'.
I can go ahead, then? No. I
have no intention of taking any
action at this time.
But Professor, he's got
very austere, good looks.
Well, how nice for
him. I'll be in touch
with you soon, Mimete.
Very good, sir. I'll be
waiting for your call.
So much for that.
Ready, Tellu?
Yes.
I really can't fault
the girl for trying...
...but she's had very
little success.
I can't keep waiting.
It's time I turned to you.
If you do well, you'll
become the next chief
officer. Good luck, Tellu.
Thank you, Professor.
You can count on me.
[growl] This is outrageous!
I won't let this happen!
Hello. Tellu speaking...
I'm sorry to have
to do this to you,
but I've decided to
cancel our plan.
[gasp]Stand by, I'll give you
new instructions shortly.
See ya!
That's kind of strange.
[giggle] The next chief
officer of the Death Busters
is going to be me!
Once I get rid of the Sailor
Guardians and demonstrate to
the Professor how
powerful I am,
he'll have to
choose me!
Thanks to you, Eudial. I
have the perfect plan.
That device you created
will make me a star.
Creepy... Yes, I definitely
sense an evil aura.
So what now?
How do we get in?
Lucky for us, they've got a
guest lecturer visiting the
campus today to
give a special class.
Meaning the school
will be open to
outside visitors like us.
This is our
chance. Let's go.
[affirmative grunt]
Huh?
This article is from four
years ago. There was a huge
fire at a genetics
engineering laboratory.
The entire staff was killed.
But Professor
Tomoe and his daughter
Hotaru miraculously survived.
They were able to escape the
raging fire in the building
without a scratch.
That's amazing.
How is that
even possible?
Hotaru is my
friend! She's good
and I won't let
you hurt her!
There's nobody here!
Well, of course
not! They're all
in the auditorium!
What's the plan? Get to work.
We start
by locating the computer room.
With any luck, we'll
find something there.
What is it, Mako?
Stop that, Mako!
What do you want?
Will you cut it out already!
What is the
matter with you?!
Keep it down! Are
you nuts?! [grunt]
[scream]
Alright, ladies. What is
it you're doing here?
We were lost,
Mr. Guard, sir...
Couldn't find the
auditorium, ya know?
It's this way.
Go to the end of the
hall, and then turn right.
That sounds easy. Don't
know how we missed it.
Hold it!
Forget something.
I can't get up, you guys.
You are such an
embarrassment, really!
Oh, now, give the
girl a break.
Huh?
You there! Where do
you think you're going?!
Me? Oh, don't mind me!
I'm nobody suspicious.
I'll be the
judge of that.
Don't move, and let me
check what's in your bag.
Ow! Hey, let go!
You're hurting me!
‐Let me see it!
‐Stop it! NO! Leave
me alone! No!
[pain yell]
Everything is riding on
this. No one gets in my way!
Sailor Moon Super!
When you think about it. The
existence of an alternate
dimension isn't that absurd.
I believe that another
dimension exists side by
side with the universe
we live in, and it
supports endless
worlds and inhabitants.
For example, here we
have a tiny nebula.
It's possible this
nebula already exists.
It could be right
before us, or next to us.
But our human mind
cannot perceive it yet.
That's not all. There
may in fact be life forms
living there, but we
cannot see them.
And similarly,
they cannot see us.
It's very likely that a
universe of unimaginable
size exists outside
of our own.
The truth of the matter is,
with our current technology,
we have no way of
confirming the proximity
of such a universe,
or even its existence.
But as our technology
advances there is no doubt
in my mind that
someday we will not only
be able to confirm
it, but experience
interaction with
alien life‐forms.
Luckily for us, the academy
staff is fascinated by this
guy's theories. So
we're able to access
areas that would
normally be off‐limits.
So Haruka, have you found
the entry to the Death
Busters operation center?
I imagine it's extremely
well hidden. Still looking.
Hm?
You scared us.
Sailor Moon and the others
are here, investigating
Mugen Academy.
Great...
This is only conjecture
on my part, but it is
conceivable that a universe
in an alternative
dimension might,
in fact, exist as a life
form unto itself.
[laughter]
The time has finally come
for our lovely universe to
rise up and swallow the
Milky Way! [laughter]
Daddy!
Be careful, Hotaru. It's
not safe to lean on that.
Take note, I've prepared
a special space for the
delicate genetic
modification
experiments we're
about to undertake.
Huh?
Daddy... What is that?
[painful screams]
Hotaru! Hotaru, talk
to me! Say something!
Hotaru! No! This
can't be happening!
[screaming]
Do you want to save
that girl's life?
If so, I can help.
What? Who?
I will save both your
life and your daughter's,
but on one condition.
You can really save her?!
I'll do whatever it takes,
just save my daughter!
I see. I'll take you at your
word. But first, I'll need
both your bodies!
[whining]
[chuckles]
Awaken, my child!
Our time has finally arrived!
Our true objective
now awaits! [chuckle]
Let's move on. We're going
to decipher the structure of
alternative dimensions.
Huh?
[chatter]
Excuse me everyone,
but I have to interrupt
this lecture to
announce that Professor
Asimov has to go now...
I do hope you'll understand.
You see? I love
the spotlight.
I love it so much that
I'm not going to let
Tellu steal it from me!
Charm Buster!
[screams]
Heh!
Daimon! Show yourself!
U Pasokon!
Good heavens! It's the
enactment of an appearance
of an alternate dimension!
[nervous groans]
So far, so good. Make
it quick, U Pasokon.
Roger!
[scream]
Time to download!
Connecting...
[pain scream]
[gasp]
Mimete!
Stop there! How
dare you try to take
the heart of an
asset to humanity!
We simply won't allow it!
The world knows
of your evil!
We are the
Guardians of Justice!
In the name of the Moon,
we'll punish you!
That's my line.
Ugh! You ladies are just
so darn predictable.
Take care of
them, U Pasokon!
I'm on it!
Prepare for attack!
Activated!
Target acquired!
Pre‐emptive strike!
[squeal]
[attack yell]
Burning...
...Mandala!
Sparkling Wide...
[fright yell]
Pressure!
Got her! No, we didn't! Now she's
hiding out there, somewhere!
[attack squeaks]
[gasp]
Venus Love Me Chain!
[giggle]
[yell]
Oh yeah?!
She's stronger
than we thought!
Don't forget about me!
Charm Buster!
[pain scream]
Mercury! Venus!
[attack cry]
[scream]
Jupiter! Mars!
[giggles] Great
work, U Pasokon!
Oh stop! You're too kind!
It truly is deserved, I
assure you. If we defeat
these girls and
return to the Professor
with a pure heart,
it will have been
worth all the effort.
So finish them off
and let's get moving.
As you command.
Not so fast, you two!
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
[squeal]
Sailor Moon! Do it!
Right!
Crisis Make Up!
Rainbow Moon Heartache!
Error! Error!
[scream]
Love‐Lovely!
[gasp]
Give it up, Mimete!
Your scheme is over!
[grunt] Don't make me laugh.
You girls barely have any
strength left to stand!
I still have my
final weapon, which
will wipe you out!
Final weapon?
Witches...
Electric Warp!
Huh?
She disappeared!
What's going on?!
[mocking laughter]
Wha‐‐ ? Where is she?
And now, we are pleased to
present Mimete on stage!
[mocking laughter]
[gasp]
[chuckle]
Surprised? Let me tell
you, it's not just my body
that's gotten bigger.
This device is also
able to amplify my power
many times over!
You should be grateful! You
people are extremely lucky
to be able to see me
on stage like this.
So, you ready?
[chuckle] You look
wonderful, Mimete.
Like a real idol.
I know that voice!
Tellu!
Yes, I'm here because
it's not nice to steal
someone else's work.
[growl] Shut up!
Don't you interfere!
Let me ask, do you know by
chance, why Eudial never
used that device?
Wha‐‐? What is that?
This? It's the power cord.
The thing is, if the power
happens to get cut off while
you're inside the
monitor, you get sealed
in there forever.
Wait, don't do that! I'm
begging you! I'll apologize!
We can work it out!
Please, just don't
pull the plug! I
don't want to die in
here! I don't want to die!!
Sorry, too late...
No!
[chuckle]
What just happened?
She killed one of
her own people!
[groan]
Super Sailor Moon!
Are you alright?!
What's wrong?!
I'm okay. I think I'm just
tired from all this fighting.
I can't believe they
eliminated one of their own!
They're ruthless!
Haruka! We need to seal off
the Messiah of Silence
as soon as possible!
No! I can't let
you hurt Hotaru!
This is no time
for compassion!
She's not a bad girl!
Enough! We told you,
we seek a different
world than you do!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'A Bewitching Flower
That Steals Hearts:
Tellu, the Third Witch."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.