This is it. Our final battle
with the Death Busters.
We have to win this fight.
We're the only
ones who can stop
the Silence from
taking over!
Don't worry Chibi‐Usa,
Hotaru...
No matter what happens, I
will save you and this planet!
We are now ready to move
on to our final phase.
[chuckle]
All that remains is for you,
the Messiah of Silence, to
place the Holy Grail
into this device.
Once it activates,
it will emit a powerful dark
light that will reach
across the Tau Star system.
The same light will then
help guide our great Master,
the interdimensional
energy being, Pharaoh 90,
into our world!
Once Pharaoh 90 appears in
this universe, everything
within it will be destroyed,
and the Earth will be
engulfed by the Silence.
[evil laugh]
The age of light, filled
with falsehoods, will soon
come to an end! [chuckle]
And in its place, a new age
ruled by absolute darkness,
begins! [evil laughter]
We have to
win this fight!
Yes! Chibi‐Usa's
life depends on it!
And Hotaru, too. It's
up to us to save them.
Right! We are the Sailor
Guardians, who fight for
love and justice!
You ready?
[affirmative grunt]
Chibi‐Usa, Hotaru, I
won't fail you this time.
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Moon Cosmic Power!
Make Up!
"The Coming Terror of
Darkness: Struggle of
the Eight Guardians!"
We don't have much time...
Our only hope is to kill
Hotaru before she awakens!
It turns out there was
no Messiah after all.
Now we have to save this
world from the Silence,
regardless of the
sacrifices we must make.
I won't let anyone
be sacrificed!
The Holy Grail is
heading this way.
You're sure of this?
The Sailor Guardians
are returning and seem
to have it with them.
[chuckle] Well,
how very convenient.
We can't let them
inside just yet.
We have to find a way
to delay their approach
until my awakening
is complete.
[gasp]
What is it?
Something wrong?
I'm not sure. For
a moment there...
I sensed a calm,
but eerie aura.
[gasp]
What?
[moaning]
I'm picking up incredible
levels of Dark Energy.
It looks to me like the only
way past their force field
is by Sailor Teleport.
Alright! Let's go for it!
[affirmative grunt]
[gasps]
[screech]
[attack yells]
Massive enemy forces
are heading our way!
Brace yourselves!
[gasps]
Here they come!
[screams]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Crescent Beam!
[screeches]
Burning Mandala!
[moans]
There's too many of them!
Damn it! They're
everywhere!
What'll we do?! We can't
Sailor Teleport at this rate!
We need to take them
out in one sweep!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[screams]
[attack screams]
It's not working!
This is bad. What
should we do?
[chuckle] Wonderful!
Mugen Academy is now
protected by Dark Energy.
It's an Omega Zone.
Now no one can set foot
into this sacred place,
without my permission.
The time has come to
take the Holy Grail!
Fire Soul!
Bubble Spray!
[groan]
[screams] Damn it!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
We all have to
teleport! Now!
[affirmative grunt]
[gasp]
[choked sounds]
[gasps]
[screaming]
Sailor Moon!
Hang on!
Grab my hand!
[scream & grunts]
[scream]
[gasp]
She's gone!
Sailor Moon!
[gasp]
[growls]
What just happened?!
I don't know, but now that
they have Sailor Moon.
There's no way we're
able to teleport.
Then how are we gonna
get inside that place?
What in the world is that?
It sure doesn't look like
an ordinary force‐field.
You think we can get in
through that opening?
[growls]
[gasp]
[attack yells]
Damn!
[painful screams]
Sailor Moon Super!
[gasp] What happened?
[gasp]
Pluto!
What have you done?
I've suspended time.
Now go. While you
still have a chance.
Why didn't you tell us you
possess such great power?
As the Guardian of Time,
this power was the one thing
I was forbidden to use.
Now I have violated
the greatest taboo.
What do you mean taboo?
What will happen to
you for doing this?
Farewell, and have
faith in the power
of the true Messiah.
[gasp] The true Messiah?
Pluto!
[grunt]
[gasp]
So they managed to
slip through by
stopping time itself?
These Outer
Guardians are more
powerful than I thought.
Yes, but even they pale in
comparison to the awesome
powers that you have
now come to possess.
And I owe it all to
swallowing the pure
heart of the sacrifice
known as Chibi‐Usa.
Hers was the purest
heart of all...
I will not let you
use it for evil.
[gasp]
Is something the matter?
No, I'm fine!
I will now go retrieve the
Holy Grail from Sailor Moon.
You take care of those two
Sailor Guardians before
they cause any
more trouble.
You want me
to fight them?!
Make use of the dolls
you've created from that
experiment of yours.
Now go! Dispose of
them, Daimon Germatoid.
[chuckle] Yes.
The Dark Energy level in
that wall is increasing
every second!
And we have no way
of getting inside.
So what now?
There's only one thing the
four of us can do. We have
to keep that wall from
expanding any further.
Let's trust that
Sailor Moon is alright.
We have a job
to do here.
And we can't afford to let
ourselves be distracted.
[affirmative grunt]
Sailor Moon!
[groaning and coughing]
Where am I?
[gasp]
Hotaru!
What the hell are those?
[nasty chuckle]
Beautiful, aren't they?
These are all the vessels
that I've created. [chuckle]
Oh, and by the way. You
two have broken school
rules by coming here.
'You must stick to
your sense of justice."
Those just happen to be
your own words headmaster.
How unfortunate. I had
high hopes for you.
Bright students such as
the two of you would
have made the perfect
vessels for our Daimons.
The same way Souichi Tomoe
was for me. [laughing]
[screeching]
He was possessed
by a Daimon, just
as we suspected!
World Shaking!
[screaming]
[laughter]
You're wasting your time,
Sailor Guardians!
I've analyzed all of your
moves and techniques!
You cannot defeat
me! [laughter]
Deep Submerge!
[nasty laughter]
[grunting]
[laughter]
[grunt]
[evil laughter]
The talismans!
What is that?!
[screaming]
I don't understand!
What's happening here?!
[screaming]
He's all yours!
[gasp]
[screaming laughter]
I thought I heard
Pluto's voice just now.
Yes.
These Death Busters are more
powerful than we thought.
You're right. But we
can't afford to lose.
[groaning]
Hotaru...
The Holy Grail...The Holy Grail?
What about it?
I overheard them talking
about it earlier...
They said if they allow
Super Sailor Moon to use the
Holy Grail in this room
then its light will purge
all evil from this world.
You must hurry. The
enemy will soon be here.
I'm really glad
you're alright, Hotaru.
[laugh]
[happy giggle]
Listen, Usagi...
You must to hurry.
Summon the Holy Grail,
so we can save Chibi‐Usa!
Huh?
Hotaru...
Tell me something.
How do you know that
I'm Usagi Tsukino?
[gasp]
[chuckle]
I thought so. You're
not Hotaru, are you?
[chuckle] I'm Hotaru,
but only in body.
[nasty chuckle]
What have you done with
Hotaru?! Answer me!
I assimilated her.
[gasp]
I am an interdimensional
being originating from the
Tau Star system,
who has possessed
Hotaru Tomoe's body.
I am Mistress 9.
[nasty giggle]
So, we've found
you, Mistress 9!
[gasp]
In order to protect the
future of this planet,
we will defeat you!
Uranus! Neptune!
Hold on a minute!
[nasty chuckles]
Huh?
[chuckling]
[chuckle] Master Pharaoh 90.
Please wait just
a little longer.
[gasp]
"Master"?
[chuckle]
[giggling]
[nasty chuckle] Pharaoh
90 is finally here!
The Age of Silence
will now begin!
No! We won't
let that happen!
It's no use. The
Holy Grail is ours.
I refuse to give up! We'll
protect this world even
without the Holy Grail!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'The Shining Shooting
Star: Saturn and
the Messiah.'
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.