They say even the most
beautiful rose hides its
thorns. Wow, that
sounds just like me!
Anyway, as long as
you're careful,
roses can be the perfect
flower to help calm and
soothe your soul. But I
guess the bad guys plan
on using them to hurt
innocent people!
Well I won't let them!
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
[chatter]
How about this one?
It's so cute!
I just love it! Thank you, Mamo!
[growl] Why are you buying
that for Chibi‐Usa?
'Cause she'll need it.
She's going on a class
field trip, you know.
That makes sense.
No one asked for
your opinion, Luna!
Come on, Usagi.
What's your problem?
Don't take it out on Luna.
You're such a baby!
Don't you know it.
Can't... Breathe... Meow!
I have an idea! Mamo! Why
don't we go on a picnic?
Just the two of us,
what do you think?!
Come on, whaddaya say?!
Hold on! That's not fair!
[arguing]
[chuckles]
[chuckle] All right,
all right, we'll go.
[giggling]
Really? Oh, you're
the best Mamo!
Oh! Hi there, Hotaru!
Wait, where are you going?
Hey, come back! I thought
you and I were friends!
Yes, we are, but...
Then let's hang
out together!
I'm sorry. I can't.
Poor kid... Sounds
like she's got some
difficult things
to deal with.
The other day, Haruka told
me not to let Chibi‐Usa near
her. But Hotaru's not a bad
girl! I just know it! Right?
Mm‐hm.
Hotaru...
'Sunny Skies After a Storm:
A Friendship Dedicated to
Hotaru.'
We must unleash my powers.
And we must hurry.
Listen closely.
You can hear
time calling to me.
Then hurry we shall, my
mistress, by offering the
pure hearts of humans!
Huh? ? Hm?
Oh, it's you. Hi again. Ms.
Kaori, Would you give this
to Hotaru for me?
Thanks so much!
Is that for me?
It was that girl again. She
asked me to give it to you.
'Hotaru, let's go on a
picnic tomorrow...'
'I'll be making lots and
lots of food for us to share
and eat. Please bring this
backpack with you, okay?
From Chibi‐Usa'.
That girl has some nerve!
She knows you're
not well, and she
still expects
you to go out.
Well, I think
it's wonderful.
Daddy?
I've been so busy with my
research, I haven't been
able to spend very
much time with you.
Why don't you go out
there and have some fun?
Hmpf.
Alright! Ready to go!
Is all of that food?
Yes! I got up extra early to
make it! [grunting]
I'm not sure it's
gonna fit in the trunk.
Maybe I should eat something
to make it smaller.
I guess Hotaru isn't going
to make it, after all.
Oh! Look, Chibi‐Usa!
Huh?
[grunting]
Hotaru!
Yay! [giggles]
So, are you coming
on our picnic?
Mm‐hm!
Oh, wow! This
is awesome!
[laughter] Hotaru!
Usagi! Come on! Hurry!
Hang on! We're
coming, Chibi‐Usa!
[giggles] Yay!
[giggles] Ahh!
[grunting]
[laughter]
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors! Rock,
paper, scissors! Rock,
paper, scissors!
I thought I told Bun‐Head to
keep away from that girl...
What made you say
that? Do you think she
might be connected to
the Death Busters?
I don't really know. But I
have a bad feeling about her.
I sense an evil aura
all around her.
Agreed...
Still, they're so cute.
[gasp]
Are you alright, Hotaru?
I'm fine.
Here I come! [chuckles]
A friend of mine works here.
He's a botanist who's
made it his life's work
to study roses.
I like roses.
You come back
here, Chibi‐Usa!
[arguing]
Yes? Professor?
Mimete... What color
roses do you like?
Aw! That's so
sweet of you!
My favorite are
deep red ones!
[chuckling]
Oh, that's not what
you meant, is it?
I'll tell you this, breeding
a new rose requires skill
and perseverance.
I understand there's a
botanist in the area who's
had great success in
raising stunning roses.
You don't say? Well that
person would undoubtedly
possess a pure heart.
Hm? Alright, Professor,
I've identified the target.
Very good. In that case, I
will create an appropriate
Daimon immediately. I'm
counting on you. [laughter]
U Bara!
Wow! These flowers
are so beautiful!
This place is definitely
incredible.
Look at all of them!
I've never seen so
many different plants
all in one place!
Hey! If it isn't Mamoru!
Katsumi! Hi!
How have you been? As
usual, you're with
some lovely ladies.
As usual?
Oh, he was just playing
around. Katsumi...
[laughter]
Papa!
I'm gonna guess
it's croquettes!
Hey, you're right!
[laughter]
Oh my! So many kids!
He's been pretty busy.
I don't know why the
Professor won't listen to
me. Targets should be
chosen intuitively.
Also, they should
be attractive.
[laughter]
Alright, you guys...
Thanks for coming,
but it's time for you
to go home and
help your mom.
Okay!
Be careful now!
Bye‐bye!
Brats... Ugh!
Alright, croquettes!
[chuckle]
So, how's that
research on breeding new
roses coming along?
Oh, not bad.
I'm almost there...
Hotaru, help yourself
to anything you want.
Thank you.
You should have some too.
Chibi‐Usa, you better
eat your green peppers.
Why? Even Mamo's
not eating them.
We'll see about that.
What are you doing?
Those peppers are
good for you!
Well yeah, except...
Eat it!
Fine! Alright, I'll
eat them, okay?
Now it's your turn, Miss
Chibi‐Usa. So eat!
Oh fine!
[giggles]
Hotaru, aren't you going
to have anything to eat?
Mm‐hm.
I just realized that I can't
remember the last time
I ate with my father.
Huh?
Sometimes adults get too
wrapped up in their work...
But you can't take it
personally. Think of it as
an opportunity to
spend more time with
your friends!
Like this...
[laughter]
You've gotta watch
your back, Chibi‐Usa!
That's what I tell my
kids, but they still
bump into each other!
[giggles]
Ah! Now that's my
kind of target.
Daimon! Show your sel‐‐
[gasp]
I'm counting on
you, Mimete!
Yes, Professor.
Sailor Moon Super!
In this greenhouse, I've
accumulated just about every
variety of rose that
grows in Japan.
Wow! All of them
are so pretty!
Are you feeling tired?
I'm okay...
It's quite a collection. But
I wanted to go even further,
so I've developed many
specially‐bred varieties,
as well.
That must have taken
quite a while.
Huh... I would never have
guessed that a guy
like him could make
something so delicate.
[embarrassed laugh]
I feel bad that
they're trapped here;
they should be growing
free outside.
Hotaru?
In here, we have a
lot of tropical plants.
Come take a look.
Hey, come on!
I'm tired. You go on ahead.
Oh...
Excuse me?
Sorry to bother you,
but can you tell me
what this flower
is called?
I'm not sure.
Why don't you ask the
expert over there?
I beg your pardon, I thought
this man was the expert.
Agh! Sorry for the mistake. You
seemed so intelligent.
I hate to ask, but would you
mind speaking alone with me?
I'm sorry, but today I'm
very busy with family.
[scream]
Oh! So these are
your sisters?
No. They're my future wife
and daughter. Excuse us.
[giggle]
Well! How rude! In that
case, I'll take his pure
heart by force!
A botanist's heart is
what I want. Don't forget.
Did you just call
me your future wife?
Why are you so excited over
something you already know?
I better go back
and check on Hotaru.
Oh yeah. That's
a good idea.
Hm!
I should probably go home
before anything happens.
What in the?! Of all
things, this is definitely
not the season for hail!
And it's pretty severe.
Uh‐oh! This is getting
pretty serious!
I'd better check
on the roses!
So, what should we do?
We should give
Katsumi a hand.
Mm‐hm.
Hotaru, you in here?
Hotar‐‐ [gasp]
[scream]
Damn...
[grunting]
Let me help...
Thanks, pretty lady.
I have to protect
these seedlings.
They're a disease
resistant variety I worked
really hard to create.
Disease‐resistant?
Breeding a rose is
not just about making
them prettier.
It's also to help
them stay healthy.
[screams]
[groan] Are you alright,
Hotaru? Say something!
Who are you?!
Sorry, but work is work.
My career takes priority
over my love life.
And that means
I'll be taking your
pure heart, old man!
Daimon! Show yourself!
[gasp]
U Bara! Bara! Bara!
Hm? This petal
has no luster.
You gave it too
much fertilizer.
[growl] How dare
you insult my petals!
Hurry up! Let's
get this over with!
What do you think you're
doing?! Hey! Stop it!
[screaming grunts]
It's a Daimon!
Moon Prism
Power Make Up!
[gasp]
You have no appreciation
for flowers!
People like you are
going to ruin this world!
I am the pretty Guardian
Trainee who fights
for love and for justice!
I am Sailor
Chibi‐Moon!
And in the name
of the future Moon,
I'll punish you!
What an annoying little
girl! U Bara, get her!
U Bara! Bara! Bara!
[scream]
How dare you use my
trademark rose attack!
And they can't be orange!
Ridiculous!
Agh! Curse you!
Don't get mad just
yet. Let me introduce
the real deal!
It's time to reap
what you sow!
I am the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
[gasp]
U Bara, get out
there and put
a thorn in her side!
U ‐‐ U ‐‐ U ‐‐ U ‐‐ U ‐‐ U ‐
Bara, Bara, Bara, Bara,
Bara! Bara, Bara!
Bara, Bara!
Every rose has it's thorn!
[scream]
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
[screams]
How can you let a tiny girl
like that beat you?!
Time to stop and smell
the roses! [yell]
[grunting]
Feel my Rose Hug!
Good! Now give them
a great big squeeze!
[screams]
Oh no! [grunting] Take this!
[yell]
[scream]
Are you alright?
What's the matter with you?!
Stop acting like a delicate
flower and teach those
little girls a lesson!
[growl] How dare you!
[yell]
[chuckle]
[chuckling]
Just finding a place
to plant my roots!
Agh! What's going on now?!
[gasp] Hang on, Tuxedo Mask!
[scream]
[yell] Can't get loose!
[evil laughter] My
beautiful bouquet!
Good work, U Bara! It
certainly took you a while!
[sceaming grunt] Wilting!
What in the world
is going on?!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Finish her!
Right!
Crisis Make Up!
[gasp]
Rainbow Moon
Heartache!
Cut down like
a common weed!
You love me not!
[gasp] I knew this mission
was a stupid idea!
What do you think
happened there?
I sensed a moment
of incredible power.
Yes, a blast of
pure darkness...
Be very careful, Small Lady.
Daddy!
Hotaru, you're okay!
Thank heavens!
Hey, what happened?
Papa, are you
really alright?
I'm fine, believe me! Say,
what was I doing anyway?
Look everyone,
it's a rainbow!
Hotaru, aren't
you glad we came?
Yeah... [giggle]
I hear Hotaru wrote
a fan letter!
To who?! Shun Hayase, the
track athlete!
Way to go, Hotaru!
The problem is,
she doesn't know
where to mail it.
Let's hand it to him
in person! I'll help!
But we can't just
barge in on him!
I'm sure that Hotaru is
willing to do anything!
You want to meet him
yourself, don't you?
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: 'Higher and Stronger:
A Cheer From Usagi!'
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.