Guess what, guess what?! My
birthday is here! And that
means cake and
presents! I wonder what Mamo
is getting me? I would
really love a pair of glass
slippers so I can feel
like a fairy tale
princess. But there's
a Daimon who wants to
ruin my special day
in a big way!
I am Sailor Moon! In the
name of the Moon, I'll
punish you.
Kaolinite...
Have you found our next
prospective target?
Yes. Without a doubt, this
is the one.
Oh my, that's very
encouraging.
This person has a heart,
purer than any of the hearts
we have ever pursued before.
I can say with confidence
that this one has a talisman.
If that's so, I shall grant
you the use of my pride and
joy, my greatest Daimon.
You're the only one I
can count on, Kaolinite.
I will not disappoint
you, Professor.
"Usagi in Tears: A Glass
Slipper For My Birthday."
Guess what day it is?
Yup, today is the
thirtieth day of June!
And it's my birthday!
How 'bout that?!
Oh? Well, congrats.
Isn't that nice. Oh!
You're having a birthday?
That means you're one
step closer to death.
You really should consider
acting your age from now on.
What?! They all must have
gotten up on the wrong side
of the bed this morning!
Hey! Wait just a second.
Isn't there something else
you want to say to me?
You're right... Even
though it's your birthday
today, make sure you're
not late for our
study session at four
o'clock this afternoon.
See ya there!
But, Bithday...
I don't wanna study!
[crying]
[chatter]
Hm?
[gasp] Glass slippers...
So lovely. If I got a pair
of those on my birthday I
would feel just like a
princess in a fairy tale.
I see it now...
...It would be like
Cinderella losing her glass
slipper, and the handsome
Prince bringing it to her.
Maybe my prince, Mamo, will
buy these for me. [chuckle]
[giggling]
Huh?
Hm?
Mamo!
Hey! I didn't expect to see
you. What are you doing
here?
[chuckle] Whaddaya think? I
came here looking for you,
Mamo.
Huh? Why's that?
As if he doesn't know.
[chuckles]Mamo's such a kidder.
He knows I
know he's shopping for
my birthday present.
Who needs uncaring friends
when I have such a
thoughtful boyfriend!
Huh? Mamo, I'm going to take all
the guesswork away and tell
you what I want you to
buy for me.
Oh?
I would like you, my prince,
to give me glass slippers,
so I can feel just like
a fairytale princess.
I saw the perfect pair in a
cute boutique right around
the corner from here.
C'mon, we should go there
right now so you can buy
them before they're gone.
Good. She's found someone to
buy her those slippers.
Hold on, Christmas is still
a long time away...
You'd better be joking, mister!
I'm not talking
about Christmas! I'm
talking about today!
Ah...
It is Hanukkah?
[growling]
[chuckle] Of course I know.
I was just teasing you.
There's no way I could
forget such an
important day!
Oh! I knew you would
remember!
[laugh] What kind of a
boyfriend would I be if I
forgot the day we first met?
[scream]
That's not it! You blew it,
you dummy! Hmph!
[chatter]
Was I at least close?
[crying]
Why the sad face, Bun‐head?
Hm?
Tears don't suit a pretty
girl like you. Take this.
Thanks Michiru...
Uh... [giggle]
Oh, that's what happened.
I think it's terrible of him
to forget your birthday. If
it were me, I'd get rid of a
boyfriend like that.
Yeah, you're right. Mamo's
no boyfriend of mine
anymore!
Hey! Does that mean I might
have a chance with you now?
Huh?!
Knock it off, Haruka. [sigh]
But I'm not even joking
around. I quite adore you,
little Bun‐head.
Uh, thanks, I guess...
Oh! I forgot! I have to be at
Rei's place by four o'clock!
Gotta go! Bye now!
[laugh] She's just so
cute...
[chuckle] She's also pretty
pure‐hearted and emotional.
She could have a talisman.
No. I doubt it...
[phone ringing]
Hino residence...
Hi, Mamoru. Uh, Usagi's
still not here yet.
Just checking again,
to see if I could talk
to her. Don't know what
I did, but she's mad.
Uh‐huh. Well, I
think I know.
Huh?You men! You always get
yourselves into hot water by
pretending you know
what's bothering us, when
you really don't understand
girls at all!
Uh... W‐What do you
mean by that?
I'll bet you didn't know
today's Usagi's birthday.
She should've told me. How
the heck was I supposed to
figure that out on my own?
I feel bad. I should never
have acted like that and hit
Mamo...
Sorry I'm late...
Did I keep you all waiting?
Surprise! Happy Birthday!
Ah! Huh?! Uh!?
C'mon! You're our guest of
honor. Your seat is waiting!
Bon appetit! Eat up! I
worked super hard on your
birthday snacks.
Here you go, Usagi. This is
from all of us. It's a
workbook to help you prepare
better for the next exams.
Th‐ Thank you, guys.
Why so quiet? You need to
liven up! We threw you this
surprise party so you
could have some fun! It's
your birthday. You're
supposed to be enjoying it!
Yeah. You're right.
And in honor of Usagi's
birthday, let's forget about
studying today, too!
All right! Freedom from
studying forever!
No, just for today!
[groan] Party pooper.
All right, everybody. Grab
your glass. Toast time!
This is so sweet. But
it just reminds me
that I won't be getting
a present from Mamo.
Now, which store was it?
[evil chuckle]
That'll do.
Welcome!
Hello. I would like to
purchase these glass
slippers.
Sure. I'll ring
them right up.
There's her boyfriend...
Shh...
And Kaolinite was
watching him.
Then he might be our next
target for a talisman.
Good Job! Way to go!
Congratulations, Usagi!
[sigh]
You seem depressed.
What's wrong?
Well, you might as well
know. I got mad and
slapped Mamo.
[gasp] I wasn't thinking. It was
one of those spur of the
moment reactions.
Usagi, did you think
that Mamoru just totally
forgot that today
was your birthday?
He didn't forget. He never
knew when your birthday was,
because you never told
him about it before.
Huh!?
Do you remember, I don't
know, ever mentioning to him
that your birthday was on
June thirtieth?
Uh, not real sure.
Maybe not.
[screams]
But if you're in love, you'd
be so in tune with the other
person, you'd just know
something like that!
Well, if that's true,
then you must know when
Mamoru's birthday is.
Of course! It's one of the
main dates I know.
Um, let's see, October tenth
is Health and Sports day.
And I know March third is
girl's day.
[laugh] I've no
idea! My bad!
[groaning]
I'm going to
apologize to Mamo.
Mamo!
Usako!
Mamo, I'm sorry.
I've been looking for you,
my Princess.
Now, let's see if this glass
slipper fits you.
Oh Mamo...
Thank you...
[screaming in pain]
What is this?
[scream]
Cenicienta!
Sailor Moon Super!
There's no happy ending for
this fairy tale! I'm here to
take away your pure heart.
Go away! Leave me alone!
Usako!
Out of my way!
[groaning]
Mamo!
[giggle]
Let go!
[grunting]
Hey! Cut it out! You're
gonna crack my face!
[grunting] Let me go!
Moon Cosmic Power Make‐!
You were going to hit me
with that? Do you know how
dangerous that is to
someone made of glass? I
could have shattered!
My transformation brooch...
[groaning]
What have you done to me?!
I turned you into glass and
now you're just like me.
See?
The Daimon got Bun‐head!
You think she was the
target all along?
[giggle]
Now don't look so scared.
Your pure heart crystal is
all I really want!
No! [scream] No!
[evil chuckle]
Uranus.. We should save her.
But what if her heart
crystal really does have the
talisman? Then what are we
going to do?
Well, knowing how you feel
about her, I guess you would
have a problem doing
anything that would
harm her.
That's ridiculous...
What's that!
[gasp]
[crying]
This light is so bright she
must have a real talisman!
It can't be true.
We've never seen a light
this intense before.
What should we do? We
don't have a choice.
If that crystal's a
talisman we take it.
Wait!
Uranus!
Once we take the talisman
away from her, we won't be
able to give it back. You
do understand
that. Don't you?
Yeah, I do.
This will mean her
death. There's no way
to prevent it.
What the...?!
And who are you, mister?
A pure heart shines a
ray of light through
the night's darkness.
I am here to be the
protector of that
light, so that it
always shines bright.
Take this!
[scream]
Usako! Wake up!
Let's go!
Hey! Bring her back here!
Usako, you must transform
into Sailor Moon.
But I can't...
Cenicienta.
Where's the girl?
Well, I had a little
problem with an
unexpected troublemaker...
You fool! You'd better find
her right away!
Yes, as you wish,
Lady Kaolinite.
Hm?
This is...
Could it be? That girl is?
[gasp] There it is.
We can't do anything about
it now. We have to retreat.
I can't just leave my
transformation brooch!
It's way too risky to try
and retrieve it now. You're
their target. We have to
keep you out of sight.
Okay...
Usako, I'm sorry. This is
all my fault. I stupidly
put you right in the
middle of all this danger.
Wait! That's not true! This
isn't your fault C'mon. We'd
better hurry up.
Yeah.
There they are!
You saw them? Yes I
did, Lady Kaolinite.
Go after them!
Right!
They've spotted us!
Save yourself! Run
away without me!
They found us 'cause I'm
slowing you down!
Don't even think that!
But, Mamo...
[evil chuckle] You
might as well give up.
It's a dead end. There's
nowhere else to run.
I know! Luna! I
need help now!
[growling]
[chuckle] You can't call
your friends now, Sailor
Moon. Too bad.
[gasp]
You sure you're all right
with this, Uranus?
Yes... I am.
Our goal is to find the
Messiah and gather up all
three talismans, in order
to save the world!
Sacrifices have to be made.
There's no way around it.
Yes, I know.
Guys, I kinda feel a little
guilty, eating Usagi's cake
without her.
Trust me. It's no big deal.
I'm sure she's out having a
great time with Mamoru right
now.
[sigh]
I'm so jealous...
Yeah, me too...
This algebra equation is
pretty hard. What a fun
challenge!
Girls, we've got a problem!
Huh?Luna, what is it? What's
going on?
Something's happened to
Usagi! She needs help now!
We're on our way! All right,
girls! Let's go!
Yeah!
Stand back, Usako...
Why? What are you gonna do?
When you see an
opening, I want you to
run for it, okay?
Let's see how
tough you are!
[chuckle] How foolish.
Cenicienta, you can play
with this silly boy.
[roar]
[grunt]
[charging roar]
You're not bad, mister!
[grunting]
Now, Usako!
I don't know if I
can do this!
Go on! Get going!
Okay!
[gasp]
[nasty laugh] You weren't
listening when I said there
was nowhere to run.
Usako!
Look at me when you fight
me! It's rude to ignore your
opponent! [attack yell]
[Attack scream]
[chuckle]
I wonder what I should
do with this thing?
[gasp]
That‐ That's mine...
I figured that. But if you
don't cooperate, I think I
may have to destroy it.
[fear gasp]
Let me have your pure
heart crystal, otherwise,
I'll crush it right
in front of you.
[gasp] Please
don't break it!
[grunting]
Usako!
Not so fast!
[grunt]
[gasp] Oh no!
Usako!
Mamo!
[nasty laugh]
[chuckling]
It's over, Usagi Tsukino, Or
should I say Sailor Moon!?
Look! Can you please
just forget I'm
Sailor Moon? No. I
pride myself on my
ability to remember things.
I even
recall what I had for
dinner last night.
Oh, well, even I know you
ate okonomiyaki!
How could you
possibly know that?!
You still have seaweed
stuck between your teeth!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "The Stolen Pure
Heart: Usagi's Crisis."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.