All it takes is to find a
little courage in your
heart, and you
too can become a
Guardian. And as long as you
have compassion for others,
anyone can become
a Messiah. But no
matter what you choose
to become, never forget
about the family and
friends that love you.
I won't let you die.
I will save you!
I'm sorry, Chibi‐Usa.
I'm so sorry.
She's finally gone.
[chuckle]
"The Shining Shooting Star:
Saturn and the Messiah."
Hotaru!
Stop calling her that!
She's not Hotaru anymore!
[chuckle] That's right.
Hotaru Tomoe is no more.
She's dead.
That's a lie!
[chuckle]
This immense power
approaching from the Tau
Star System, is none other
than the Ruler of Silence,
Pharaoh 90. Our true
Master of the Death Busters.
And once I have the
Holy Grail, Pharaoh 90
will appear and the
Age of Silence will
finally begin. [chuckle]
We will never let
that happen!
We'll stop you here!
World Shaking!
Deep Submerge!
No!
[scream]
Why, thank you.
You fool!
Why'd you do that!
[giggling]
[grunting] Dammit!
[screaming]
If you don't want to see the
two of them killed before
your very eyes, hand
over the Holy Grail.
Don't do it!
[gasp]
Shall I eliminate
one of them right now?
Please wait!
If you hand over the Holy
Grail. I'll despise you for
the rest of my life!
Don't do it!
Sailor Moon!
[chuckle]
No don't!
Hotaru...
[gasp] Mr. Tomoe!
You're alive.
[painful grunt] Hotaru...
Hotaru, it's me...
Your father.
Hotaru...
My little girl. What
have I done to you?!
You're no longer
Germatoid...
Take your filthy hands off
me, you pathetic worm!
[grunt]
[gasp]
[grunting] Hotaru...
[gasp] No, please! Stop
it! I'm begging you!
Just stop!
[roars and growls]
The Daimons are
getting stronger!
Our shield needs
more power!
Hang in there!
We can't allow them
to get into the city!
[roar]
[grunting] Hotaru...
Daddy...
[gasp]
Impossible!
Hotaru?
[gasps]
The body's rejecting me?!
[groaning]
Daddy! [grunting] Help me!
Finish her off now,
Sailor Moon!
No!
She's there!
Hotaru's alive!
I know it!
She's fooling you!
[sobbing]
Hotaru. How can I
help with the pain?
Holy Grail.
Holy Grail?
Without the Holy
Grail I'll die...
[gasp]
Don't leave me, Hotaru.
This Holy Grail
that you speak of.
Where is it, Hotaru?
Daddy!
[scream]
Sailor Moon, what
are you doing?!
You can't do this! You're
not even the Messiah.
It's not your right to
give away the Holy Grail!
But Hotaru is still
alive. I've gotta save her!
I refuse to accept a world
that can only be protected
by sacrificing a young girl.
I won't allow
it! It's wrong.
There it is!
That's the Holy Grail?
Please let me have it.
For Hotaru's sake.
Thank you so much.
Hotaru, I'm holding
the Holy Grail.
Is this what
you wanted?
Yes. Quickly...
Hmph.
[nasty laugh]
[scream]
[fear gasp]
Thank you,
Sailor Moon.
You gave me what I needed
to welcome Pharaoh 90
into this world. As a
show of my gratitude,
I will allow you to live
on as a Daimon vessel.
Hotaru, can you hear me?
You're still there, right?
Hotaru!
[grunting]
It's too late.
There's nothing
you can do now.
I won't let you
people have your way.
Not with Hotaru, or
anything else in this world!
Just give it up.
You have no chance of
winning, now that I have the
Holy Grail which is a power
source of raw emotion.
Love, hatred, hope and
fear, packing enough
energy to wipe out
the entire planet.
[giggle]
Only a pure heart stronger
than the Holy Grail can
defeat Pharaoh 90.
But that's quite
impossible since there is
no pure heart crystal
with that much power.
Now watch, as my Master
assimilates the Holy Grail!
[crazy laugh]
[gasp]
I can't hold out
much longer now!
[scream]
They're too strong!
No!
[laugh]
Come this way,
Pharaoh 90!
Look! There's the
result of your selfish
need to have to
save everyone!
Moon Cosmic Power!
[scream]
You're unable to do a double
transformation anymore.
You have no power
to stop the Silence.
The new world ruled
by the Master and me,
is about to begin.
No!
Sailor Moon Super!
[grunting and screams]
Hotaru...
Daddy?
Hotaru?
Daddy...
Yes, sweetie.
Daddy, it's
dark. I'm scared.
Where are you?
I'm right here.
I have to save
Chibi‐Usa.
Daddy... Get me
out of here!
I wish I could. But I don't
know how. I'm sorry...
If only we could go
back to happier times.
[sobbing]
[giggling] Daddy!
Hotaru!
Daddy!
Aw, Daddy!
[sobs] Daddy...
Daddy...
I'm so sorry...
Daddy?
Huh?
[gasps]
Ho‐ Hotaru?
[growling]
[scream]
Get away from me, you worm!
Why don't you just die!
Your life is meaningless!
It amounts to nothing!
Don't get in our
way! Be gone!
Perish! Perish!
No!
Never!
Curse you! [growl]
I won't let you
control me!
There are people
that I love, that I
want to protect...
[gasp] I won't let
you hurt any of them!
[gasps] [screaming]
Ho‐ Hotaru!
The Guardian of
Destruction, she's back.
[gasp] Huh?
Are you?
[gasps]
Chibi‐Usa, you're
going to be all right.
Sailor Saturn.
Hotaru?
Thank you, Chibi‐Usa.
For everything...
Pharaoh 90 is going
to enter our world.
Now, we no longer have a
way of stopping the Silence.
Hotaru!
[roaring]
[screaming]
All our efforts to try
and prevent the world
from being destroyed
were for nothing.
[sob] It's over...
Sailor Moon.
Are you happy now?
Answer me!
Sailor Moon...
[gasp]
I want to thank you for
trying to protect me.
Until the very end...
Sailor Saturn...
Ho‐taru?
Hotaru!
No, I'm no longer Hotaru.
But I am the only
one who can save the
world from the Silence.
Leave the rest to me.
Wait, let me help you!
No. It would be difficult
even if you could transform
into Super Sailor Moon.
But the power of the Holy
Grail belongs to Pharaoh
90 now, so it would be
impossible for you to
even go in there with me.
To defeat Pharaoh 90,
I'll have to enter its
core and destroy it from
within. It's my duty.
But after you defeat Pharaoh
90, what happens to you?
I'm called the Guardian of
Destruction because I have
the forbidden power
to destroy planets.
But when I use that
power, I too must
perish along with it.
No!
Goodbye now...
Hotaru!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[grunt] Crisis Make Up!
Crisis Make Up!
Come on, transform!
[screaming]
Crisis Make Up! [sob]
Sailor Moon...
[sobbing]
Crisis Make Up!
Goodbye...
Have faith in the power
of the true Messiah.
The true Messiah.
[grunting]
Huh?
[groaning]
Wha‐?
Sailor Moon, you handed over
the Holy Grail to the enemy
and awakened the
Guardian of Destruction!
Your selfish actions
nearly cost us this world!
I can't forgive
you for that!
Haruka, please stop! I
thought we had gotten
past our differences!
Not as far as
I'm concerned.
We need to settle
this once and for all.
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "A New Life: Parting
of the Stars of Destiny."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.