The Mugen Academy is hosting
the next national practice
exam. Of course, Ami's
attending, since studying
is her passion! I really
wish it was mine, too!
Anyway, try not to jinx
her by using words like
'failing', 'dropping out',
or 'falling behind'
around her, okay?
Because if you
do, then...
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
So Tellu was a student
from the Mugen Academy?
Looks like we were right
about that place...
Something's going
on there.
Yes. I agree.
Hey! Ami!
I just saw the last national
practice exam results...
Huh?
Yeah! Great job!
Congratulations! You got
another perfect score!
Wow! Way to go!
Thanks, but I wasn't the
only student whose score
was perfect. There was one
other girl who aced the
exam, too. Her
name is Yui Bido.
And she's the top
ranked student
at the Mugen Academy.
There's that Academy again.
Hey, isn't the next national
practice exam going to take
place there in just a few
days? I think we should go
ahead and try to sneak in
during the exam and find out
more about that school!
But how are we gonna get
inside the building this time?
I doubt that will be a
problem while the exams are
going on. We'll just have
to mix in with the crowd
and act like we
belong there.
We just need a ticket to
get us through the door.
Yeah, well I've got one...
To tell you the truth, I've
been studying for the past
several weeks
to take the
national practice
exam there.
Ooh boy!
Well, I guess that means
we're all set to go!
"Believe in Love: Ami the
Kindhearted Guardian"
Whoa...
All these kids are waiting
in the snow to take an exam!
They're sure serious
about their studies.
Unlike someone we know.
[angry growl] Hey! Ya
don't have to rub it in!
That's quite a
large turn‐out.
Yes...
The Mugen Academy
has become popular
because of its
competiveness.
It attracts only the
best and brightest.
Heh?
There are some who don't
quite fit that description.
But the enthusiasm
these kids have for their
education is impressive.
Professor!
Hello Viluy.
It looks like your
preparations are moving
along quite smoothly.
Yes...
Once everyone is assembled
in the exam room, I will be
able to gather a great
number of pure hearts.
Good. You've conceived
an ingenious plan
to help awaken the
Messiah of Silence.
Thank you, sir. I promise
not to disappoint.
I know my priorities. Unlike
someone who's more into
flirting than doing her job.
Oh! Hey Mamo!
Hey, where are
you headed?
Somewhere!
Hotaru!
Hotaru...
Where are you?
[chatter]
[laugh]
We were all able to sneak
in without being detected.
These kids all
look possessed.
Yeah they're making me
feel a little uncomfortable.
I don't think you should
judge them so harshly.
They're just studying
hard so they can follow
their dreams. Nothing
wrong with that.
They're all studying
so they can follow
their dreams, huh?
[groan]
In comparison to
them, I must look
like a real lazy bum.
Maybe you should have
thought of sooner.
Kinda late to
regret it now!
What kind of
friend are you?
That was your queue to tell
me that I'm not a lazy bum!
[laugh]
Aren't you Ami Mizuno?
Huh?
You always get such
amazing scores on these
practice exams.
What an honor to
finally get to
meet you in person.
And you are?
Yui Bido. I had the
exact same score as you
on the last national exam.
Oh! You're the
girl who tied Ami!
And who are you?
[laugh] Nobody important.
Just a great friend of hers.
Well, if you're her friend,
then I'll bet you work very
hard every day, side
by side with her.
So what's your
best subject in school?
I'm good at napping.
And eating lunch.
Oh! You're quite
the kidder.
So listen, Mizuno, there's
something I wish to show you
while we wait for the
exams to start. Come on!
Oh, um, uh...
Teen years are supposed
to be fun too, you know!
There's more to life
than constant studying!
Usagi...
Hm?
Let's split up in twos
and check this place out.
‐Later!
‐See ya!
The waves are stirring. The
sea is beginning to rage.
Your intuition
tells you that?
Yes. I'm getting an
extremely bad feeling.
I'm picking up on it too.
There's a mysterious and
eerie energy surrounding
this building. I've
always felt it.
And today, we're
going to find out why.
Are you thinking of
checking out that
underground room again?
Yes...
And this time, we'll
make sure to uncover
all of their secrets!
What is this?
It's a miniature universe.
The science class made
it per my instructions.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes...
It's the Tau Star System.
The Tau Star System?
Our school is divided
into five departments:
Philosophy, Performing
Arts, Science,
Athletics, and
Pre‐Professional.
In addition to the regular
teaching staff at the Mugen
Academy, students with high
grades are also instructors.
That's why I teach
the science class.
You teach students
here even though you're
a student yourself?
Yes. Like I said,
anyone who scores high
grades can teach.
It's what makes this
Academy so unique
and special.
But just because you get
good grades, doesn't
necessarily mean you'll
be a good instructor.
Excuse me?
In order to be good at it,
you need to understand the
feelings of all students,
even those who aren't
doing well, and
encourage them. So they
can enjoy learning...
[laugh] So naive!
Look, logic is all that's
required in science,
or any other class.
There's no need to care
about others feelings.
Well, I think you're wrong
about that. Even science
benefits from the
warmth of a human heart.
Wow, you've sure got some
silly notions for someone
who has one of the best
test scores in the nation.
Well the exam's about to
begin. Perhaps I'll see your
warm heart later, Mizuno.
[laugh]
This girl, Ami
Mizuno, was it?
I sense something
suspicious about her.
Let's keep an
eye on that one.
There's a good chance
that she might be one
of those Sailor Guardians.
I, Science Class head
instructor, Yui Bido, will
uncover her true
identity! [giggle]
As Viluy, Member
of Witches 5!
I can handle this myself!
[gasp]
Professor, since I'm
overseeing this operation,
it's logical that I
make sure there are
no interruptions.
If Ami Mizuno is a Sailor
Guardian, and she and her
friends get in my way,
I'll get rid of them.
But I was‐‐
Will you just
shut up already!
These nano robots are
quite extraordinary.
They've been programmed
by me to faithfully
obey my every command.
Let me give you a tiny
demonstration. [chuckle]
Ahh...
As you can clearly
see, I have everything
under control.
I'm putting all
of my trust in you.
Do whatever you
think is best.
Yes, sir!
Why did you even bother
coming back from the dead?
Was it just so you could
stand around pining for
the Professor? 'Cause
he doesn't seem to
notice you're here!
[laugh]
Is something
wrong, Kaolinite?
It's nothing...
By now everyone's
concentrating on the exam.
It's time, my nano robots!
Gather the pure hearts
of each and every
one of these students!
So far, so good. Nothing
looks suspicious to me.
Yeah. Everyone seems
focused on the exam.
[cries of pain]
Oh no, look!
Their pure heart crystals!
Well done! I shall offer
these pure hearts to the
Messiah of Silence!
Looks like we were right!
This is the enemy
hideout for sure.
What'll we do, Minako?
Seems like someone here
in this building is
controlling the computers.
We have to find that
person and stop them!
Let's go and
tell the others!
Right!
Sailor Moon Super!
This is where the evil aura
seems to be originating...
[gasp]
The Messiah of Silence!
The ultimate evil we
must eliminate her!
Wait!
What are you doing here?
I won't let you harm her!
Listen, she is the
ultimate source of evil.
She will plunge this
world into silence if we
allow her to live.
That's not true. Hotaru
is a poor tortured soul.
An innocent child
being manipulated
by the Death Busters.
It's so naive for you to
pity her. While you plead
for her life, the entire
world will be led to ruin.
You're wrong! You need
to leave her alone!
Move!
You need to get
out of our way!
No! I won't let you
lay a finger on her!
What are you
doing down here?
This area is strictly
off‐limits to outsiders.
Michiru Kaioh, Ami
Mizuno, and Haruka Tenoh.
How suspicious!
Show your true selves!
Yui Bido is...
Mosaic Buster!
[scream]
Haruka! Michiru!
Stop it!
Go! Don't worry about us!
What are you talking about?
I can't just
leave you two here.
How illogical to risk
your life to save them.
I guess your kindheartedness
will be your downfall.
Take this!
Mosaic Buster!
Mercury Star
Power Make Up!
I knew it!
Protected by Mercury, the
Planet of Water, I am the
Guardian of Wisdom.
Sailor Mercury!
So the girl genius turns out
to be a Sailor Guardian.
Can't say I'm the
least bit surprised.
Shame on you for
misusing science!
Shut up! You'll die along
with those other two!
Mosaic Buster!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
[gasp]
Nice try!
[grunting]
[chuckle] Does it hurt?
The nano robots I've
programmed are so small,
they're invisible to the
human eye, but they're
eating into your body
and tearing it apart.
Very soon all that will
remain of you, is your
beautiful pure heart.
It's wrong to use
science for the purpose
of hurting other people...
It's supposed to help them!
Well, it'll sure
help me when I offer
your pure heart to the
Messiah of Silence!
I won't let you have
Mercury's pure heart
or anybody else's!
Huh?!
Agh! The Sailor
Guardians!
I can't allow you to steal
pure hearts from hard
working students
focused on their studies.
Just so that you can
use them for your own
selfish purposes!
I am the Pretty
Guardian who fights for
love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
Hmph! How nice of you to
come. But understand this.
If any of you make
a move, she dies!
[gasp]
Mosaic Buster!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Help us!
Uranus Planet
Power Make Up!
Neptune Planet
What the‐?!
World Shaking!
[scream]
Deep Submerge!
[pain scream]
[grunting]
Crisis Make Up!
[gasp] Super Sailor Moon!
I'm done playing
games. They end now!
Rainbow Moon Heartache!
My precious nano robots!
Eliminate Super Sailor Moon!
[pain scream]
Agh! What's going on?!
You're attaching yourselves
to the wrong person!
Stop! You idiots! Don't
you recognize me?!
They don't care about you.
No need for
feelings in science.
Isn't that what
you told me?
[pain scream]
[moaning]
Well, apparently
Viluy failed.
Such a waste...
Nice of her to
do herself in.
Saves me the trouble
of eliminating her.
Well at least now I know
the true identities of the
Sailor Guardians!
Is this her punishment for
believing that science is
just logic, with no love?
The poor thing.
[gasp] The
Messiah of Silence!
Hotaru!
[gasps]
Sailor Guardians...
The battle has just begun!
[evil chuckle]
Hotaru!
Uh? Mamo... Puu...
Aren't you cold?
No.
How long are you
going to stay?
Just a little
while longer.
I want to be here when
Hotaru comes back.
I miss her. I just want
to see her face again.
Chibi‐Usa...
Small Lady...
Ami Mizuno, if you hadn't
interfered with us back
there, we could have defeated
the Messiah of Silence.
Your naive kindheartedness saved
her, and allowed her escape.
But that same kindness
saved us, as well.
So, we just want
you to know...
How very grateful
we are to you...
[laugh]
[giggling]
[nasty laugh] At last! The
purest heart of all is now
in our possession!
Not Chibi‐Usa! Give it
back! Return her heart!
Now our moment of
victory has come!
Awaken, Messiah
of Silence!
Hotaru!
She's no longer Hotaru.
Observe the power of the
Guardian of Destruction!
Next time on Sailor Moon
Super: "Shadow of
Destruction: The Messiah
of Silence Awakens."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.