Minako, you sly girl. Why didn't
you tell us you had a cute
boyfriend back when you were
on the school volleyball team?
Now he's being targeted by a
Daimon! How dare you attack the
pure heart of an athlete who
plays for the joy of the sport!
I won't allow it!
I am Sailor Moon! In the name of
the Moon, I'll punish you!
You want us to get
matching outfits?
I think it'd be cute. That store
in Shibuya had some nice ones.
You don't think the
idea's a little tacky?
Yeah, it's very tacky.
Come on, it's
just one outfit.
Okay, it'll be a memento of our
time together in middle school.
Ugh, boys are such push‐overs,
this is nauseating!
Hmph!
"I Want to Quit Being a Sailor
Guardian: Minako's Dilemma."
Where do you
wanna study today?
How about the city library?
Come on, hurry up babe! We're
gonna miss the movie!
You're going too
fast, slow down!
Well! Whoop‐dee‐doo, aren't you
cute couples!
Hey, Artemis.
We just finished inputting all
the data we have so far about
our new enemy.
But the computer wasn't able to
come up with any definite
answers.
So the bottom line is, we
still have no clue as to what
those Daimons really are, or
where they're coming from.
[Sighs]
Here I am in my final year of
middle school, and suddenly,
I'm having doubts about
the direction of my life.
What we lack most right now is
solid information. It's very
frustrating.
What I lack is something else.
And that thing is love!
Huh?
"When you stare at love, the
love also stares back at you."
I can't remember the name of
the philosopher who said that.
Mina, nobody ever said that.
Fine then! But why can't a
wonderful boy with a bouquet of
roses come to me and say...
"May I ask, would you consider
being my date tonight?"
Yeah! Why can't something
like that happen?!
I wouldn't hold my
breath, kiddo.
But when? When will that magical
moment happen to me? Don't I
deserve it?
Oh, sorry!
Oh! Asai!
Aino!
Thank you.
So I see you're still with
the volleyball team.
Yeah, at least until the
summer tournament.
After that I'll be too busy
studying for the high‐school
entrance exams, so I want
to make sure we win.
Gotcha.
Well, good luck!
Thanks.
Hey, Aino.
What?
Well, I was just wondering, why
did you quit volleyball after
you came back from England?
Hmm.
That 'flying dig and flip' move
you used to do? It was really
awesome.
You gave up playing
so suddenly.
Yeah, volleyball was great, and
I really did like being part of
the team.
Tsutomu! Get back in here!
You're holding up the game!
Huh?
Okay!
Guess I should get back to
practice. See ya!
Kay, bye now.
Mina.
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
Huh!
[Giggles]
Professor, your tea is ready.
Hmm?
I know you like cookies,
so I baked you some.
I appreciate your consideration,
Kaolinite. But tell
me, have you found the
all‐important talismans yet?
No.
I hate to bring this up...
...but have you considered
the possibility that you
continue to fail because your
search methods are faulty?
I have failed. I'm sorry.
Working so many hours, all this
research is taking a terrible
toll on my body.
Lack of exercise weakens a
person. Hold on, that's the
key! They say healthy hearts
reside in healthy bodies!
Wait a minute!
Maybe that's it!
What if you were to target
pure‐hearted young athletes who
have a passion for sports?
Sounds like a
wonderful plan.
[Giggles]
I'll get to work and send
forth a new Daimon right
away. Perhaps I'll get
back into sports, myself!
What sport do you
especially enjoy, Professor?
Rhythmic gymnastics.
Uhh.
[Heavy Breathing]
Morning!
Well, hello there!
You seem to be unusually early
for someone who's always tardy.
I'm overcoming that
particular problem.
I see.
Tell me, Aino, do you
have a boyfriend?
[Gasps]
Why do you ask?
Oh, no reason, I was
just wondering.
Hmm.
And what about you? Anyone
special in your life?
Oh, uh well, sort of.
See I'm looking for a girl to
date that I can play sports
with, otherwise I don't think
it would really work out.
Hmm.
Actually...
What is it?
Remember our first year, when I
was still on the reserve team? I
had such a crush on you.
But you were already our best
player and I was totally blown
away by your skills.
I decided I couldn't tell you
how I felt until I was part of
the starting line‐up.
What?
Wow! Good one!
I almost fell for it!
Uh, you were kidding, right?
Don't you still like
playing volleyball?
Oh come on. I'm
already a third year.
So? What does that have
to do with anything?
Look, I don't have time for
sports. My schedule is
jam‐packed.
With school work?
Actually, with a lot
of things.
Ah, I see. That's too bad.
Okay, well, I gotta
go to practice!
Two, four, six, eight! We're the
ones who dominate!
[Grunting]
[Laughing]
Usagi, take a look!
This is so funny!
Show me later.
See? This panel! Where Sailor
V's about to reveal her
identity!
Hmm, I don't care.
Right! Sailor V is so pretty!
Under her mask, of course.
Oh wait what am I saying of
course she's pretty she's
modeled after me!
[Laughing]
What's the matter with
everybody? You're so down today.
I've got just the thing to perk
you up! You're really going to
enjoy these!
I bought you all Sailor V diet
chocolates and Sailor V vitamin
drinks!
Come on, guys! Enjoy!
Okay.
Oh! It says I'm a winner.
Congratulations, you lucky girl!
With three of those
winning wrappers, you get
a special Sailor V badge!
Really? Guess it's my
lucky day. Thanks.
Minako.
Hmm?
You're having quite a hard time
concentrating on your work.
Ha! There's that strict
school teacher coming out again!
I'm so sorry, Ms. Ami.
Minako, the guardian of love
and justice, is a bad girl
who doesn't like to study.
I even cheat sometimes. And the
funny thing is, I don't care.
[Sighs]
Maybe I'll quit the Sailor
Guardians for a while.
[Gasps]
Don't act so shocked.
I'm just kidding.
I'm sorry I don't feel like
studying today. I'm going home.
Mina.
Hey, Artemis! Look at
this cat, huh!
I don't see a cat.
There is no cat.
[Grunts]
Now she's gone!
You dummy.
You're hopelessly insensitive,
you know.
Sometimes you just have to give
a girl her space, Artemis.
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
Come on, let's go!
[Grunting]
Aww!
[Gasps]
Hey.
Oh, hi, Haruka.
What's going on? You usually
do a lot better than that.
Hmm.
So tell me something, Haruka, do
you have a boyfriend?
We already talked
about that.
Oh, right. But you do at
least have someone.
Hmm.
Do you feel like being a racing
prodigy limits you on who you
can be in a relationship with?
You're so gifted, do you feel
like you can only date people
as special as you are?
What exactly are you
trying to ask?
Just this.
Don't you ever wonder how
things would be if you
were nothing more than an
ordinary high‐school girl?
I mean don't you ever feel like
you're missing out on normal
everyday happiness?
Minako, are you feeling you've
sacrificed normal everyday
happiness?
Uh, no.
[Chuckles]
Honestly, when I think about
it, I've never wondered what
'ordinary happiness' is like.
But since I don't think I'm out
of the ordinary, it must be
whatever I feel day to day.
I am who I am and I'm
just fine with that.
I'm happy to be me.
I fell in love with racing
years ago and knew it
had to be part of my life.
I never questioned it.
And in the pursuit of that
passion, I found something much
deeper than happiness.
Does that make sense?
I'm not sure, but
I think so.
Hate to do this,
but I really have to go.
I'm sorry for putting you on the
spot with all my questions.
Oh, that's okay. It was no
problem, really.
Let's have a rematch back at
the arcade one of these days.
See ya around!
'Something deeper than
happiness.' Yeah.
The seas are restless again.
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
Hey, what's happening? Are you
going home without me again?
Yep! See ya!
[Gasps]
Don't forget, we have
a date this Sunday!
I'll be there! Bye now!
See ya then!
[Gasps]
Haikyun!
[Screams]
Everybody! A Daimon
has appeared!
Venus Star Power! Make Up!
Serve!
Look out!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
Hold it right there!
Huh?
[Grunts]
I am the Pretty Guardian of love
and beauty, Sailor Venus!
In the name of Venus,
I will punish you!
With the power of love!
How dare you interfere!
Serve!
Venus Love Me Chain!
You're wasting your efforts!
Nothing you do will work on me!
What!
Net violation!
[Grunting]
What a fool! You might have
lived longer if you weren't such
a silly Sailor Guardian!
[Grunting]
[Gasping]
All right, young man! Time
to take that passionate
heart crystal right out
of your healthy body!
[Screams]
Asai, no!
Not again! There's no talisman
in this heart crystal!
Hah! We've wasted our time,
Haikyun. Kill Sailor Venus
and that boy, too.
As you command.
All right.
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
[Laughing]
[Gasps]
What was that?
Timeout! I'm here to punish you
for unsportsmanlike conduct!
You have no right to prevent
someone from living their life
to the fullest!
I am the Pretty Guardian, who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
[Grunts] Haikyun,
get rid of her!
Right.
So, Sailor Moon, can
you crush this ball?
Don't Sailor Moon! That ball
is made of Asai's pure‐heart
crystal!
[Gasps]
What should I do?!
Serve!
Mars!
Hmph!
How'd you like that
interception?!
Great move!
I call a foul!
What in the world?
[Screaming]
[Screams]
[Laughing]
It's too fast!
Dodging is all
we can do!
How are we supposed to stop an
attack like that?
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
I'll receive! You and me,
Daimon!
Hmph!
All right! Get ready 'cause here
comes my special attack!
Lightning bolt!
Serve!
I am a Sailor Guardian. There
are things only I can protect.
[Gasps]
Game on!
Hmph!
What?!
[Cheering]
I've seen that flying 'dig and
flip' move!
So that's it! Sailor
Venus is really...
Hmph! Ready Sailor Moon?
Yeah!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[Screams]
Go Team Japan!
We did it!
That was awesome, Venus!
Looks like we missed the
game this time around.
Yeah.
Hah!
Come on! I think we should
go to a concert instead!
I'd love to, but it's too
late to get tickets.
Aino.
Hey there!
I wanted to ask...
Hmm?
If you ever have the chance to
meet Sailor Venus in the
future...
I was hoping you could maybe
tell her, thanks for saving
my life.
Huh?
Doubt I'll see her. But if I do,
I'll be more than happy to pass
your message along.
Hmm.
Come on, let's go!
Okay, bye!
[Giggles]
Oh, Miss...
May I ask, would you consider
being my date tonight?
[Giggles]
Sure, but it's gonna cost
you a fortune!
Seriously?
[Laughing]
Stupid, stupid, Mamo!
What are you so worked
up about this time?
He completely forgot my
birthday! Can you believe he
would do such a thing?
That's terrible!
Right?!
You told him when your birthday
was and then he forgot about
it anyway?
Huh? Well, now that
you put it that way...
Usagi!
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"Usagi in Tears: A Glass Slipper
for My Birthday."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.