"Dear Uasgi. How are you? You're
so lucky. You get to see Mamo
whenever you want."
"I miss him so much. I've
decided to come back and pay
everyone a visit. See you soon!
Sincerely, Chibi‐Usa."
What in the world?! I don't
believe this!
In the name of the Moon, I'll
punish that brat!
"The Arrival of a Small
Pretty Guardian."
[Ringing]
Hello. This is Witches 5.
Yes. Just one moment, please.
This is Eudial speaking.
It's me. I just wanted you to
know I've looked at your report.
What did you think?
Hmm. It's quite interesting.
Thank you very much.
Based on the specifications
you see there, I've already
found the next pure‐hearted
talisman candidate.
I expected no less
from you, Eudial.
This particular target is a girl
who's known for her taiko
drumming.
Her pure heart may
well be a talisman.
I'll leave it to
you to find out.
I'm prepared to alter our
retrieval approach, as you
suggested in your report.
I'll provide a Daimon to assist
you, one that is designed with
your target in mind.
Soiyaaa!
[Screams]
Hey, everybody!
I was thinking we should
all go to the Juban Festival
tonight!
That's a great idea!
Right?!
Sounds like fun! We can
all dress up in yukatas!
Oh yeah! Sounds great!
It's okay, right Ami? It won't
hurt if we just take one night
off.
Besides, since Rei's not
around we really shouldn't
study without her.
Mhm!
Okay, I guess we do need a break
once in a while.
[All] Alright!
Actually, what's going on
with Rei, anyway?
She never cancels our sessions
at Hikawa Shrine. And she didn't
even give us an excuse.
Maybe she's on a date.
Huh?
[Crashing]
[Moaning]
Oh that really hurt. [Moaning]
Was that?
Rei?
Miss Hino!
Hi there! Sorry I'm late!
You don't have to apologize.
I just got here myself.
She's with a woman.
That's right. And who was it
that was so sure she was on a
date?
Well the truth is you never
know! It could easily still
be date.
Wait, what if it's actually the
reverse, and that's really a
man dressed up as a woman!
I don't know, it really
doesn't look that way.
Well we've got to find a way
to get closer. I can't
eavesdrop from this far away!
What do you say?
Will you do it?
Well, I'm not sure.
We need your help! I really
don't know how we can move
forward without you!
Now which one of you
ordered the blend.
That's mine.
[Sighs]
Hmph!
[Grunting]
Is something wrong, miss?
[Grunts]
Was it just my imagination?
Hmm!
Can I help you, miss?
[Sighs]
Hmph!
What's happening? Miss?
[Screaming]
That's hot! My scalp's on fire!
What are you guys
doing following me?!
Miss Hino?
Yes!
About that matter,
I'll help you out.
Really you will?
Sure. It would be my pleasure.
[Sighs] That's terrific! I can't
tell you what an honor this will
be!
The Juban Festival Liven‐Up
Committee?
What is that?
Exactly what it sounds like.
We're in charge of livening
up the festival.
That's interesting, I didn't
know you were a member of that
committee.
How did you get
involved, Rei?
Well, a friend of my grandpa's
just insisted I participate this
year.
That's a likely story. I bet
that you actually volunteered,
right?
You love putting on a show. You
were just putting on a show a
second ago.
That's ridiculous! That
was all your fault!
Now, now, take it easy. These
kinds of things happen.
Like they say, even with four
feet, a donkey may stumble.
It's horse, not donkey.
Whatever.
[Humming]
[Sighs]
I'm just glad Ms. Tohno
accepted my invitation.
Tell us already, who is she?
Someone very special.
Her name is Maya Tohno, and she
happens to be a very talented
taiko virtuoso!
Taiko?
So is that why you canceled
our study session? To
ask her if she'd perform
at the Juban Festival?
Of course! If Ms. Tohno
performs on the taiko...
It'll take the Festival to
a whole new level!
Ohh! Rei, how about you let
me play the taiko, too!
Believe me, there's no taiko
you could ever play!
Hang on, now that I think of
it, there is one you could play.
Oh, really?!
[People Talking]
[Drumming]
Goldfish! Come and
try to scoop the goldfish!
Scoop the goldfish! It's
fun for everybody!
[Sighs] With all the things
we could be doing at
this festival, how did we
end up selling goldfish?
You're very good! You've bonded
with that taiko! It's perfect!
You give it a try!
[Giggles] No thanks I couldn't.
Anyways, you were the one who
said you wanted to play.
[Grunts]
This one feels sturdy!
Thank you!
Now, just scoop it up!
Like that!
Mako, Ami, we're not gonna make
money if you help them!
Hey, old lady!
Get movin' and bring
us some nets!
And make it fast!
We don't got
all night, y'know?
Did you call me old?
[Grunting]
Fine! Here you go!
[Gasping]
[Groaning]
[Giggles] What could have
gone wrong?
Goldfish! Catch your
goldfish...!
Hey there, Bun‐Head.
Hmm?
Haruka! Michiru!
[All] Hey you guys!
What's going on? You're
all working here?
Well, sort of. Hey!
Since you're both here, would
you like to try scooping
goldfish?
Okay, I'm
up for it!
Why not.
Right this way!
It was kinda fun catching that
cute little goldfish.
Did you just call it cute?
What? Are you jealous
of the fish now?
[Chuckles] Maybe I am.
[Grunts] I'm telling you they
make everything look easy!
All right, I'm gonna
give it a try!
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
Was that just my
imagination?
Huh? There she is!
Hey Rei!
Keep it down!
What for? Just how long are you
gonna make us tend that stall!?
Shh!
Hey, that's Ms. Tohno.
Yeah. She's been practicing that
drum for over three hours now.
Huh?
I can't believe she's doing
this for free. I told
her she didn't have to
spend so much time on it!
But she said that she has to
stick to her routine. She
can't play well unless she
gets herself psyched up first.
[Drumming]
When I first saw her
playing the taiko...
...I thought she was
exactly what I needed to
make the Festival the
biggest success ever.
But now, I realized I was just
looking for a short‐cut.
Huh?
Watching someone with her
incredible talent prepare,
has really taught me a lesson.
And what was that?
That I need to work even
harder if I want to succeed!
Right!
I think it's high time we shake
things up around this place!
That sounds like
a great idea!
Yeah! [Giggling]
This is the place. The data says
the target is somewhere in this
vicinity.
Guess that means I'll
just have to call her.
Hello! Hello! Testing, testing,
one, two, three!
Paging Maya Tohno. Maya Tohno,
if you are present, please show
yourself.
Maya Tohno, Maya Tohno. Again,
if you are present, please show
yourself.
Huh?
There she is!
[Gasps]
Gottcha!
[Screams]
She's taking Ms. Tohno's
heart crystal!
Transform!
Hmm!
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
Mars Star Power! Make Up!
Great. I'll be taking that
crystal now.
I don't think so!
Anyone who targets the pure
heart of a taiko drummer
is an enemy of traditional
Japanese performing arts!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
That's right! And I am the
Pretty Guardian of love and
fire!
I'm Sailor Mars!
And in the name of Mars, I'll
chastise you!
I see. So you're the Sailor
Guardians, is that right?
I, of course, am Eudial
of Witches 5!
Did you say Witches 5?
Never heard of it.
Daimon! Show yourself!
Soiya!
Huh?
Soiya, take care of these
nuisances for me.
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
[Screams]
[Screaming]
[Laughing] Dance! Soiya! Soiya!
[Laughing] Huh?
Answering the call from a new
era. Sailor Uranus here, to
fight with brilliance!
Also answering the call from a
new era, Sailor Neptune here to
fight with elegance!
Drop that right now! Take your
hands off my crystal!
Too bad. Your first foray is
about to end in failure.
Say what?
Unfortunately, this pure‐heart
crystal isn't a talisman.
Darn it! Soiya! Take care of
these interlopers, will you?
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
[All] Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
So you're not gonna go
help them this time?
They can't always expect us
to save them. We're not
their babysitters.
Yeah, you got a point.
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
Soiya!
Huh?
[Grunts]
Now that I'm all warmed up, it's
time to play the taiko!
Huh?
Uh, by playing...
Are you referring to us?
[Laughing] Ready?
[Screams]
Nothing personal, but could you
start with her first?
Why did you say that?
Because what she's about to do
will be painful, why else?!
Hold it right there!
Uhh.
Now who is it?
It looks like you girls
can't manage without me,
after all. You really
need to pull it together!
I know that voice.
I am the Pretty Guardian Trainee
who fights for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name of the future
Moon, I'll punish you!
[Both] Huh?!
Chibi‐Usa?
Fine with me! I'll just
get rid of you first!
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
Huh? What the?
Why isn't it working?
[Grunts]
Oww!
Aww, what's the
matter, kid?
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
Huh?
I did it!
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
Finish her, Sailor Moon!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[Screams]
Lovely!
[People Talking]
Hey! I still can't see! Do
something about it!
I'm carrying you, isn't that
enough?! Now stop complaining.
Well, well, aren't you cute.
Oh! Hi!
Wow. I've gotta say your little
friend looks a lot like you,
Bun‐Head.
[Both] We don't look
anything alike!
She just happens to
be a cousin, that's all.
Ladies and gentleman...
Ms. Maya Tohno's taiko
performance is beginning here on
the main stage. We're all set!
Take it away, Ms. Tohno!
[Cheering]
By the way, Chibi‐Usa. Why
exactly did you decide to
come back again?
Mommy sent me. She said I had to
go to the 20th century to train!
What?!
To train? What's that supposed
to mean?!
I'm back everybody! Nice
to see you all again!
Tell me again why you
had to come back?
Mommy ordered me to! She said
to go and make friends in the
20th century!
Make friends, but don't
make trouble, okay? We have
enough on our hands with
our mysterious enemy!
Oh my gosh! That
boy is so cute!
Are you even listening to me?!
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"Making New Friends: Chibi
Moon's Adventure!"
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.