It's summer vacation!
Time to play and laze
around in the sun. But
instead of playing...
...Mako is working hard doing
some intense physical training
at a temple in the mountains.
I wonder what that's about.
What's going on, Mako?
You don't have to keep
your worries to yourself,
you know. Don't you forget,
we're here for you!
[Heavy Breathing]
[Grunting]
Damn it! How could I have let
her beat me like that!
Ironder!
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Physical strength is my forte!
[Grunting]
[Screams]
Dammit!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
Lovely!
I need to up my training
so I can be stronger.
[Heavy Breathing]
"I want Power: Mako
Lost in Doubt."
Put me through
to Eudial.
Eudial speaking. I've already
been busy pinpointing our next
target, Professor.
Excellent. So who are we
after this time?
A Getsuren Buddhist monk by the
name of Kakusui Yakushiji.
He's been living in the
mountains for the last
four years, on a quest
to attain enlightenment.
A heart as pure as his is quite
rare in this day and age.
Hmm.
By the way professor, can you
tell me what the talisman looks
like?
If a pure heart crystal is
indeed a true talisman, it
will take the form of a
mirror, a sword, or an orb.
These are the Three Sacred
Treasures.
Once these treasures are brought
together, then the Holy Grail
will appear.
Daruma!
[Screams]
Huh? Mako sent
me a postcard.
Hmm. It says she's spending the
break training at a temple in
the mountains.
Training?
[Gasps] I don't believe it!
According to this address,
she's staying at a temple close
to where Mamo's working!
Huh?
Oh, Mamo took a summer job
working at a resort hotel.
[Giggling] What a lucky
coincidence.
You're not thinking of...
[Eating Loudly]
[Sighing]
Wow! This is great! I really
love traveling. There's nothing
else to do but eat!
Don't you think you should
try and slow down a little
bit? You're acting like you
haven't eaten in days.
[Sighing]
I'm starving. How about
something for me?
I'm kinda hungry
too, Mina.
Open wide.
Ahh.
[Chewing]
Hey, Usagi. How come Chibi‐Usa
didn't come along with you?
As her future mother‐to‐be,
I kindly asked her to just
stay at home this time,
and she happily accepted.
You big liar! You said you were
gonna use the bathroom and
instead you snuck out the back
door and left without me!
Take that!
[Grunts]
Well, she might be
a little upset.
Now according to the guide
book, there's supposed to be
a wonderful hotel that's not
too far from the temple.
Oh! There, that
must be it!
Wow, it looks luxurious!
Why don't we stay there instead
of at the temple?
I thought the whole reason we
came out here was to stay with
Mako and help her train.
But if we stay here, we'll still
be close to her without
interrupting her training.
We can run over and help her
out whenever she needs us.
You actually make a
good point, Usagi.
As long as we have a place to
get our studying done, then I
don't mind.
New plan, we'll
stay here!
Stop!
Come on Usagi, tell them why you
really wanted to come here.
Wait a minute, what's
Luna talking about?
I have no idea.
She proposed this trip because
Mamoru's working at that hotel.
So then, all your big talk about
wanting to come here to help
Mako train...
...and wanting to get away to
study hard...
...was a fat lie!
Well, not exactly. I wouldn't
call it a lie.
I just thought this trip
would be a lot more fun if
we all had things we wanted
to accomplish. Huh? Huh?
Let's go back to our original
plan. We're staying at the
temple.
[Sighs]
[Heavy Breathing]
I wonder how many
steps there are?
Compared to the
Hikawa Shrine.
52.8 times as many.
I think I broke
my lungs.
[All Moaning]
[Grunting]
[All] Huh?
[All] Mako!
Huh? What are you
all doing here?
We missed you! And we thought
you could use some help with
your training, so here we are!
Huh?
How could you just leave and not
tell us where you were going?
We'll do anything to help. Just
tell us what you need!
[Giggles] Huh?
[Heavy Breathing]
[Screams]
Isn't he truly amazing?
He runs up and down this
mountain area at least fifty
times a day.
Oh, Mako. Can't fool me, you've
fallen in love with that monk!
Huh? What? No, it's
not like that!
Well, back to training!
[Winces] Even though it's
summer, this stream water's ice
cold!
Please allow me to join you.
[Wincing] I can't!
What do I need to do to
become like you, Kakusui?
Right now, I'm in
a terrible slump.
I can't give you the specifics.
But my skills don't work against
my opponents.
I think that if I could develop
your kind of willpower, to
withstand the ice cold water,
I could get out of my slump.
Why won't you talk to
me? Say something!
I'm so cold. Can't move my lips.
What?
[Sneezes] I hope I
didn't catch a cold.
[Laughs]
That smile suits you. I'm glad I
made you laugh.
Huh?
"No other path makes me feel so
alive. Thus it is the one I
take."
That's my favorite saying.
"No other path makes me feel so
alive." I think I get it.
But even once you've chosen your
path, you will still question
your decision the moment you run
into the slightest problems.
Especially when
training gets tough.
What? You question
yourself too, really?
[Laughing] Probably a whole lot
more than most people ever do.
I've found my target. [Laughing]
Tell me, Mako. What made you
decide to come here? Why did you
suddenly want to train?
Uh, there was no
particular reason.
Oh, you sure? Well let me know
if you want to talk about it.
It's best not to keep
things to yourself.
Guess you should know.
Especially since you're such a
secret schemer!
Oh yeah! Well you're just
a big meanie!
[Grunts] Why you!
[Screams]
That really hurt.
Improve your aim!
[Grunts]
[All Screaming]
[Snoring]
Everyone came all the way here
to help me. But I need to
work this out on my own.
That's the only way to do it.
[Grunting]
It's so noisy!
It's Mako!
I don't think we should
interrupt her while she's
right in the middle of
training exercises.
I agree.
Is this breakfast?!
[Sighs] How am I supposed to
start the day with just this?
I read somewhere that eating
small portions will boost your
brain's potential!
And with this perfectly balanced
meal, you're bound to get
healthier!
They're right. This'll
be good for you.
I don't wanna worry about
my health when I'm on
a trip, I just want to
eat lots of good food.
Looks like Mako's already
gone out to train.
Aren't you guys
gonna join her?
Screw this! Let's go to the
hotel for a real breakfast!
[Groans]
Can't you ever think of
anything else but food?!
You don't have to get so bent
out of shape about it. It's just
the way I am.
All right already. Let's
go to the hotel.
Yay!
What are we gonna do about this
food? I hate leaving it out here
and letting it go to waste.
It won't! I'll
eat it!
I'll bet there's a
hotel pool. Ta‐da!
Wow! You sure came prepared.
Actually, I did too!
I've got mine right here!
Check this out, sunflowers!
Guess Ami's the only one who
was serious about coming here
to help Mako.
She's always
so selfless.
[Giggles]
I brought one too.
[Sighs]
[People Talking]
Ah! Now this is what I call
a real meal!
[Slurping]
Hi Mamo!
Huh? Usako? What are
you all doing out here?
What a coincidence! Never would
have thought I'd run into you
here!
[Sighs] Usagi you're a
terrible liar.
Hey Mamo! Let's hang out
after you're done there.
Sorry, I'm afraid I don't have
any time for that.
This job pays really well, but
there's a lot to do, and not a
free moment!
Chiba, I need you right
now, c'mon! Table six!
Coming!
[Sighs] Boy, that
really sucks.
Hey, she's cute!
All of them are
super cute!
That one is
totally hot.
Maybe we should
go talk to them!
Her eyes seem to
be drawing me in!
I can't stop
staring at her!
C'mon, let's go
over and say hey!
Wait a minute. Look at those
girls over there! They look even
hotter!
Hmm? Let's go!
What's up,
hotter chicks?!
Who's hotter than us?!
Look! Haruka and Michiru are
here, too! [Laughing]
Oh.
Hey, you're here
too, Bun‐Head?
Yeah!
Nice to see you!
What a coincidence!
Your swimsuit's gorgeous, wow!
Well thank you. But your suits
are pretty amazing, as well.
Guess we all look amazing and
gorgeous. [Laughing]
Usagi, why don't we
start heading back?
I think I'm gonna stay here
a little bit longer.
Usagi, Mamoru can't spend time
with you no matter how long you
stick around!
Busted! You have
no reason to stay!
You think you're so smart!
Well I've had it! [Screams]
Uh‐oh.
[Screams]
A wind has come up, carrying a
damp ocean smell. Something is
about to happen.
Mhm.
[Sighing]
Rei was right. Mamo didn't even
have one minute to spend with
me.
Huh?
Hmm.
[Snoring]
And he's sleeping.
[Yawning]
[Laughing] Looks like
I screwed up there.
I thought you were meditating
on your inner strength.
It's important to relax your
mind once in a while, to
recharge your thoughts.
[Laughing] Guess I
relaxed too much.
Huh?
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
Get down!
Gottcha!
[Screams]
[Gasps]
[Gasps] No! Kakusui!
Everyone needs support.
Don't push yourself.
Believe in others.
Kakusui!
[Grunts]
Jupiter Star Power! Make Up!
Moon Cosmic Power! Make Up!
Huh?
Anyone who tries to harm Kakusui
will answer to me, Sailor
Jupiter!
[Laughing] Well in that case,
I've brought along a Daimon to
keep you busy.
Daimon, show yourself!
Daruma!
Hmph!
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
Hold it right there!
Huh?
No matter how many times you try
to defeat us...
...we the good guys, will always
pick ourselves up and fight
to protect the innocent!
I am the Pretty Guardian, who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
And the rest of us will
chastise you as well!
I want you all to
leave this to me!
[All] What?
I have to defeat
her by myself!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Daruma!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
[Groaning]
[Laughing]
Oh!
Thanks for your efforts, but
unfortunately this isn't a
talisman.
[Grunts]
She sure made
a hasty retreat.
[Grunts]
Hey, want
some help?
No thanks. I'll
do this myself.
Don't hurt yourself
or anything.
Daruma!
[Screams]
[Attacking Scream]
You're not alone, Jupiter! We'll
do this by combining our powers!
We five together,
make one!
We're stronger as a group!
Let's fight as a team!
Everyone needs support. Don't
push yourself. Believe in
others!
All of you are my strength. I
know we can do this!
Yeah!
[Gasps]
[Sighs]
Da‐da‐da‐da‐da!
Ap‐pu‐pu!
[Gasps]
It's important to relax your
mind once in a while, to
recharge your thoughts.
[Inhales]
Daru?
[Screams]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Daruma!
Da!
[Sighing]
[Chewing Loudly]
The only worry Mako has now is
getting enough to eat!
Back then, my dream was to
become one with the wind.
You sure are
poetic, Haruka!
What about you, Bun‐Head?
What are your dreams?
Me? My dream is to
be a pretty bride!
That's a cute dream.
Oh! Also I want to be a baker, a
florist, and a flight attendant!
Whoa. You sure spend
a lot of time dreaming.
[Snoring]
Bun‐Head?
Next time on Sailor Moon Super:
"The Bond of Destiny: Uranus's
Distant Past."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.