[BARRY] Damn, girl.
You're short again.
Heh. You are one useless
bitch you know that?
Why don't you try bringin' in
some real money for a change?
Hey! The fuck you lookin' at?
[slap]
[phone ringing]
[BARRY] I know that
sweet little ass of yours
can earn more than this!
[BARRY]
You hear what I said?
[slap]
[BARRY] You don't like
gettin' smacked around,
you'll find some
more johns, you get me?
Get me?!
Now don't you go running
off on me, Alex.
[WORICK]
All right, all right!
Too slow.
Same ol', same ol'?
[NICOLAS]
Mm.
[phone ringing]
[WORICK sighs]
[WORICK]
Yello.
Thanks for calling,
you've reached the Handymen.
[ALEX humming]
[PUNK B growls]
I feel so bad to keep
pesterin' you Handymen.
Here, for your trouble.
Thanks.
[WORICK]
You know,
this neighborhood's been
gettin' kinda sketchy lately.
I worry about'cha, Granny.
[JOEL] Nonsense, I'm a
tough old broad. I'll be fine.
Besides, you fellas scare
most of the thugs off.
S'why I like you.
[WORICK chuckles]
[JOEL] Since you're here,
I got another job for ya.
[WORICK]
Huh?
Can you boys run
a package for me?
Shouldn't take you too long.
Ah, sorry, Granny,
wish we could,
but we're supposed to
meet with Chad after this.
[JOEL] All right. Well, tell
Inspector Adkins I said hi.
Heh. He'll be thrilled to know
you can still fog a mirror.
[JOEL]
Eh?
[WORICK]
Aw, yeah! Jackpot!
Sweet haul! Not bad
for a minute's work.
Good lord.
Makes me think you're
the real thugs.
Just promise me you
won't pick on the weak.
'Course.
[JOHN A]
Ah, shit!
--[slap]
--[ALEX grunts]
What now?
[JOHN A] Bitch, I ain't payin'
you to bite down on my dick.
Ugh. Screw this.
Shoulda gone to
the damn brothel.
Found a respectable girl.
Hey, floozy!
How many times I gotta tell ya?
This is the off-limits zone!
You shakin' your ass
here hurts my shop.
Take it someplace else!
She come around often?
Oh, yeah.
Been seeing more and
more unfamiliar faces
comin' and goin' lately.
They treat this place like it
was their own little playground.
[WORICK]
That so?
Damn, she is stacked.
[JOEL] She's in with
those idiots there.
I'm telling you,
I've friggin' had it.
All these kids around here now,
they don't know the first thing
about the rules of this city.
Sign of the times, I guess.
[MONROE] All right,
if there are no objections,
I say we get today's
meeting started.
[MONROE]
Ah, interesting.
[CORSICA]
Hm?
The gang causing so much
trouble in town lately.
Those wouldn't happen to be your
boys now, would they, Corsica?
The ruckus last
week on 7th Street.
That was their doing, I believe.
[CORSICA]
Use this to clean up the mess.
And cool it with
the wild accusations.
Yeah. We'll match that.
[chuckles]
Three grand, eh? Very well.
Should be more than enough
to set things right.
So, Monroe, who you gonna
hire for the cleanup job?
A neutral party, of course.
[CORSICA]
Neutral?
[MARCO chuckles]
[CORSICA]
Hmph.
No one in this godforsaken
town is "neutral."
[MONROE]
Hm.
Forget about it. I'll take care
of all the arrangements.
What, wanna trade?
Yeah right.
[groans]
[WORICK]
Mm! Damn, that's good.
No one makes navarin
like Granny Joel.
[CONSTANCE]
Got that right.
So, what 'bout Chad?
S'not nice to make a cop wait.
[WORICK]
Oh, it's fine!
This here is our delivery fee.
And I intend to savor it.
What's with the damage?
Someone gave your place
a good goin' over again.
That from last week?
You noticed, didja?
This town is balls.
Bastards raise hell outside
the shop and steal my guns
whenever they can.
[WORICK]
Who are they? Got a name?
Some upstart gang that's
started terrorizing
the whole damn neighborhood.
I tried bringing it up to Chad,
but he doesn't seem to care.
I'm at my wit's end here!
--[door opens]
--[WORICK] Hm?
[CONSTANCE] Oh, wait!
If I can just tough it out,
the Four Fathers'll take care
of 'em eventually, right? Uh!
You dicks! Don't eat it all!
She sent that for me!
Ugh! Way to just
help yourselves!
[CHAD]
They're late.
Those two are always up
to somethin'. Or nothin'.
[CODY] Well, Chad,
I'm thinking they stood us up.
We should probably
cut our losses
and head back to the station.
There's plenty of other work
piling up on our desks.
And you smoke too much
these days, you know that?
[CHAD]
And you sound like my old lady.
Jeez, Cody, get off my nuts.
Do-gooders ban smokin' in
the station, make me a criminal.
Just let me enjoy this.
Hey, hey, boys.
What naughty cops you are.
Skippin' work,
smokin' in alleys.
Hey, don't include me in that!
Least I can keep on
schedule. You're late.
Just you? Where's
that mute, Nicola--?
[CHAD yelps]
Jesus, don't scare me
like that, asshole!
[chuckles]
[WORICK]
Sorry, he can't resist.
So, what do you need
from us now, buddy?
[breaking glass]
[PUNK A chuckles]
[BARRY] So a guy with one
eye and that puny Asian
beat your asses, and you
think the best response
is to run back here
and cry to me?
[PUNK B] Barry--
U-Uh, sir! We're sorry!
[BARRY grunts, gasp]
[CHAD]
Name's Barry Abbot.
His little outfit has
stepped up activity recently;
trying to expand their
territory and reach.
Even started doing business
in the off-limits zone.
We'd love to take this creep
and his whole crew
down ourselves, but...
[WORICK] Too much pressure
coming from above
and your hands are tied.
Sounds like a certain someone
who loves making trouble
is pulling the
strings again, huh?
[CHAD]
Exactly.
Which is why I'm
asking you clowns
to deal with Abbot's operation.
How many men?
[CHAD] Depends on when
and where you hit 'em.
But I'd guess, long as you avoid
their hangout, no more than ten.
Thirty-five hundred. You in?
[WORICK]
Huh.
Well, not sure.
That seems a bit lower
than our usual cleanup fee.
Hm. What do we
do about the girl?
[CHAD]
I said the whole crew.
How come? Ya know this broad?
[WORICK]
Nah, nah.
It's just... can't the
police keep her safe?
Like protective custody, or...?
Buddy, you're gettin' soft.
Don'tcha realize how many
women and children like her
live in this city?
There's no end to 'em.
[sighs]
We can't be playin' favorites.
Gotta keep things neutral
to protect ourselves.
Start giving special treatment,
n' we piss off the Four Fathers.
Then it'll be our
heads that roll.
[WORICK] Eh. Yeah I get it,
but killing a woman?
That is such a downer.
If you don't want the gig,
better tell me now.
It's fine, we need the cash.
[CHAD]
You're a child.
Huh?
[WORICK]
Oh.
He's askin' if you're cool
with us keepin' a trophy.
Yeah, all right. That's fine.
Just don't take anything
anyone can ID.
[WORICK]
Don't worry.
Won't be anything
that'll be missed.
Yeah. What about the bodies?
Nope. This time, we'll
take care of disposal.
You guys just focus on
doin' what you do best.
[NICOLAS]
Mmm.
[CHAD]
Then it's a deal.
I'll give you the rest
when you're done.
[WORICK]
Right.
[CHAD]
Hey!
This is the biggest
job in a while,
so give it to 'em good
and hard, Handymen.
[BOTH chuckle]
[WORICK]
Roger that.
[BARRY grunting]
[CODY]
So, um. Is Nicolas, you know...?
[CHAD]
What? You just now noticed?
Some detective you are, kid.
[CODY]
Hmm.
I guess... I just figured
he wasn't much of a talker.
Ya gotta watch your ass
around that guy.
Yeah, his hearing
may be for shit,
but his eyes are
as sharp as hell.
So if you got something
private to say,
you better cover your lips
or else he's gonna know every
damn word outta your mouth.
[BARRY] Spread this around
the off-limits zone.
We'll take the rest
over to District Three.
[CAPO A]
Hey, Barry.
What gives? You takin'
orders from Corsica now?
You know well as I do District
Three is Monroe family turf.
That's the point.
We're gonna snatch
that territory
out from under their feet.
Once the Monroes fall,
the Cristianos collapse
right alongside 'em.
[CAPO A] Then the Corsicans
after that, huh?
Get ready, boys. With those
crews outta the picture,
Ergastulum will be ours.
[CAPO A]
Like the sound of that!
[THUGS laughing]
Yo.
[ALEX]
So yeah.
Can't avoid ya today,
huh, Handyman?
Yeah, it's funny.
We don't usually see
each other's faces,
'cept through the window.
Been seein' you around
here for a few months,
but I never heard your
voice till just now.
[ALEX] I'm sorry.
I, uh, got this kinda dirty.
No bigs; it's not mine.
[ALEX]
The other guy's, then?
Yep.
[ALEX]
Oh. Please tell him I say...
No way. Y'know sign language?
[ALEX] Just from watching you.
That's about all I know, though.
[chuckles]
[WORICK]
Why are you with that asshole?
[ALEX]
Got nowhere else to go.
Sucks, right?
You should leave.
He'll be pissed at me.
[WORICK sighs]
[WORICK]
Hey.
Hate to break it to ya,
but Barry's not comin'
'round here no more.
[ALEX]
Huh?
Barry?
A damn Tag?
[BARRY]
Shit!
What the fuck's
a Tag doing here?
[CAPO A]
No good! It's a dead end.
Barry, this is fucked.
There's no way out!
Don't move! Don't you dare move!
Wait, hang on! Stand down!
I really don't feel like
takin' on a Tag today.
Tell me who hired you and
how much they're payin'.
Whatever it is, man,
I'll double it, I swear!
Hey. You listening to me?
[inaudible]
Shifty move you
pulled there, Nic.
Starting without me like that.
Y'know, I coulda sworn
I told your ass
to sit tight till I got back.
Hold up.
You're the one who made
me go after the girl
in the first place
'cause you didn't wanna.
She said thank you
for the hankie.
Uh?
[BARRY groans]
Sorry. Guess my aim is
just a little bit off today.
But it'll only hurt
for a minute.
So grit your teeth
and bear it, will ya?
[BARRY screaming]
[BARRY groaning]
[WORICK] Hey, easy, Nicolas.
No need to be cruel.
I'll feel bad if
he suffers too much.
[BARRY]
Hey, gimme a second.
[WORICK]
Hm?
The hot girl.
You're looking for
the brunette, right?
Take her. She's all yours!
And drugs.
You can go ahead and
take the whole stash, too.
If that's not enough,
I have money!
Lemme fill you in on
what's really goin' down.
Idiots who get rich
breaking the law,
scumbags who get off
hurting women,
those are the kind
of guys... that we love.
Love... to death.
[WORICK]
You fall into both categories.
Your folks must'a been proud.
[BARRY]
Please, no--!
[gunshot]
You came.
Thought you'da make
tracks outta town.
Damn you. You took
it all away from me.
Now what the hell
am I supposed to do?
[ALEX] I was finally ready...
to stop fighting it.
[ALEX crying]
[crying continues]
[WORICK]
Mh-hm.
[growls] Nico!
[ALEX crying]
[CHAD sighs]
[WORICK]
Hey, hey! Chad-ster!
Oh, hey. You're actually
on time for once.
[CHAD]
Aw, what the hell, Worick?
Please tell me this a joke.
That better not be the
girl from the picture.
Translate?
[WORICK] You told us we were
allowed to take a souvenir
from the job.
Well, I'd like you to meet...
Alex, our shiny new trophy.
I don't think this violates
the spirit of our deal.
What? No! Urgh! I am so sick
of you two dickin' me around!
[WORICK] Oh, relax.
There ain't no harm done.
[CHAD]
Yes there is!
The mafia won't turn a blind eye
to you helpin' one
of their damn runaways!
[CODY yelps]
[NICOLAS growls]
[NICOLAS]
What a pain.
Sure, Chad, we may be
indebted to you and the kid.
I get it.
But we don't take
orders from you!
I don't want you getting
the wrong idea. All right?
To take, one must first give.
If you don't let me and Worick
have what we want for once,
I worry the next head I separate
from a body might be yours.
Intense, am I right?
So you gonna let us
keep her, Chad, or what?
[growls]
Ah, fine. Do whatever
the hell you want with her.
Friggin' hate workin' with Tags.
Here's the rest o'
your money. Take it!
Wait you're... a Tag?
Pleasure doin' business with ya.
I'll buy ya dinner sometime.
[CHAD]
Tch.
I swear, those guys are more
trouble than they're worth.
Take me back to the station.
[CODY]
Oh, right!
[CHAD]
You got paperwork!
[WORICK]
Hey! Alex!
Down there again? How's tricks?
I gotta go do
a thing at a place.
Can you help out in here?
[ALEX]
Hmm?
Doin' what?
[phone rings]
[ALEX]
Hello.
Thank you for calling.
You've reached the Handymen.