[TV ANNOUNCER A] ...announcement
made earlier this afternoon.
The move came in response
to the recent string
of Twilight slayings in the city
as well as revelations
that have come to light
regarding widespread violations
of their fundamental
human rights.
Appalled by stories of physical
abuse and sexual exploitation,
slavery has been abolished
with a new set of
Three Laws imposed...
See ya, Wallace.
[WALLACE]
Hope you hire me again sometime.
[TV ANNOUNCER A] Seen as a
deterrent to criminal activity,
these Three Laws...
[WALLACE] Hey, Nic!
Wanna grab something to eat?
We can try that fancy
place on the main drag.
The client I was just with
says they'll even serve
Twilights there, too...
[TV ANNOUNCER A] Twilights
are those individuals born
with the residual
genetic effects
of the bio-enhancement
drug Celebrer,
which was used in the
East-West War of Unification
before it was--
[CHAD]
They're gonna start enforcing
those Three Laws today.
Should go and pay your
respects to Danny later.
Least now you guys won't have
to feel quite so ashamed about.
[NICOLAS mumbling]
[CHAD]
Huh?
What was that?
[NICOLAS]
It's no use. Any of it.
Oh, heya, Ginger.
Here to see the boss?
[GINGER]
Y-Yeah.
[phone ringing]
[HAUSEN]
Hi, this is the Paulklee Guild.
Uh. 'Scuse me, S-Sir Paulklee.
[PAULKLEE]
Spit it, Ginger.
It's, it's, um...
Doug's taken a job w-without
the Guild's permission.
And it s-seems he had
a run-in with the Handymen.
[PAULKLEE]
The Handymen?
So, what kind of job was it?
[GINGER] Uh... Um, yeah,
that's the thing.
H-He's been hired
to kill Boss Monroe.
[PAULKLEE]
Huh?
[WORICK]
I just need you to answer
a couple of questions
for me, that's all.
For starters, who is it
you're workin' for?
And second,
what's the game here?
What kinda scheme
you try'nna pull
on the Monroe and
Cristiano families?
[PUNK C]
Go to hell, man. Seriously!
I ain't no goddamn rat!
You... You ain't gonna
get away with this--
[YANG]
Y-You want us to bet on 'em?
How can you say that, Boss?
That Tag Nico's fighting is
ranked just as high as he is!
We gotta help 'im!
[MONROE]
Oh, Yang.
Gunfire only gets in the
way for guys like them.
[YANG]
But, Boss...
All right, Miles,
which one ya want?
I'll take the Handyman.
Diego. Which one?
[DIEGO] Uh. Here, I'm
putting my money on the kid.
Hey, last call to place
your bets, guys.
Delico, aren't you
gonna say some--
[YANG]
Delico?
[DOUG]
Ha-ha! Finally.
This is it. This is what
I've been waiting for.
An A/0 who's
not in the Guild!
[DOUG]
Aw, shit yeah.
So glad I took the
assignment to off Monroe!
Holy...
Whoa.
[MONROE]
How many years has it been?
There was this one
clueless Twilight
who tried to bring down the
whole family all on his own.
He was just 14 at the time.
Had "C/3" engraved
on his scorched tags.
Of course,
it wasn't the first Twilight
attack we'd had to face.
But even Normals like us
could usually handle
a little bit of trouble.
Plus, back then,
the family had two guys
we'd hired from the Guild.
A B/2 and a B/0.
Though that false
sense of security
would bite us in the ass.
We did manage to bring
down the little prick,
but by the end of his attack,
the mansion was in shambles.
It was quite the scare.
How'd he do so much damage?
You sure he was a C/3?
We never heard all this.
Well, of course not.
While we were
fightin' off that Tag,
you two were still pissin'
the bed at the orphanage.
[MONROE] Yeah, and you haven't
even heard the best part.
His reason for hittin' us
was pretty hysterical.
Had nothin' to do
with bumping me off
or even stealing valuables, he--
He wanted revenge
against a Monroe goon.
Guy'd beat the hell
out of his friend.
And all this friend did
wrong was rock the sheets
with the girl the
goon was datin'.
You're here.
Well of course.
You're our best client.
[YANG]
Hey, Ricky!
You took your sweet time.
Yeah, sorry, I had
to make a stop first.
[MILES]
And what'd you find out?
[WORICK] Not sure if
you noticed this or not,
but the dudes attacking
are with the Corsicans.
Bullshit.
There's no way the Corsicans
bring in a Twilight for help.
[WORICK] Apparently, the
family's younger members
wanna make names
for themselves.
This hit is their bright idea.
[MILES]
Hmm. Dumb kids.
They're not thinkin' long term.
[WORICK]
Got that right.
Trouble is their stupidity
came with a catch.
[DELICO]
Hm?
A catch? Like what?
That Tag's a wild card.
[WORICK]
Ooh.
[YANG] Okay. I really think
we should help, guys.
Keep 'em!
They're a thank you gift
for breakin' my knife.
But to be continued, big guy.
I gotta finish the job
they hired me for.
Getting Monroe's head!
[YANG]
Damn it! Again?
Aw, hell. Grab Monroe!
[MONROE]
Always on task, that Nicolas,
even when facing
one of his brothers.
Such a good boy.
[WORICK] Hey, partner!
We're Handymen, not garbage men.
You're hurtin'
our brand's image!
The kid's comin' back.
Hey, wait a sec,
are you wearing my shirt?
You dick!
That was expensive, man!
[DOUG yells]
[WORICK groaning]
Dammit. Be a little
more gentle next time.
[WORICK]
Wait! Nic!
Ah, hell. Not again.
[NICOLAS]
He didn't hit the nerve.
That had to be what
he was aiming for.
I gotta end this soon.
Before the Celebrer wears off.
[WORICK]
Nic, hold up! Nic!
That idiot.
Doc Theo's always warnin'
him to stop this shit.
It destroys his sense of pain.
[DOUG]
Damn, that hurts!
What kinda dumb fuck grabs
a guy's blade with bare hands?
I was wrong.
If I wanna take out Monroe,
I will have to take out
this bastard first.
[MILES] Hey, should your pal
even be doin' this?
[WORICK]
Nope. Absolutely not.
[MILES grumbles]
As a matter of fact,
Nic OD'd on Celebrer again.
[MILES]
That is bad.
[DELICO] So that's how Nic's
not even fazed by his injuries.
[WORICK] Miles, I need ya to go
contact the Paulklee Guild.
[MILES]
The Guild? Does that mean--?
[WORICK] Yeah, that Tag up
there's affiliated with them.
His name is Doug.
So if we or Nic kill him,
we'll really be up the creek.
[MILES] I understand.
No argument here.
[WORICK]
You better jet.
There's a shortcut up
that set of stairs.
[MILES] Right. Stop by
once you've fixed all this.
[WORICK]
Will do.
Mr. Monroe, always a pleasure.
I hate to leave like this.
That little Tag really
made things interesting.
[MILES] It's dangerous out here,
and you know it. Let's go.
[MONROE]
Oh!
One more thing, Worick.
About what you said earlier,
you got a key detail wrong.
When he came at me years ago,
it wasn't "revenge
for a friend,"
it was simply a Twilight
defending his contract holder.
Hmph. Well, I consider
us good friends.
Whether he does, or not.
[DELICO]
So, does that mean
that C/3 in the boss's
story was actually...?
[ALEX humming]
Looks like it might rain.
[DOUG grunting]
[MONROE]
When he came at me years ago,
it wasn't "revenge
for a friend,"
it was simply a Twilight
defending his contract holder.
[WORICK]
Dammit, that's aggravating.
Old bastard's right.
I know he is.
Boy, do I know it.
But how am I supposed
to stop this?
I mean, I gotta do somethin'
before she shows up.
Huh... Maybe I could
take out the kid's legs.
[footsteps]
[yelps]
[WORICK]
Too late!
[CHAD]
All right. I understand.
So, uh, what did the
Monroe family want?
[CHAD]
They said one of the attackers
was a member of the Guild.
[CODY]
Huh?
But... I thought Mr. Monroe
was fully protected.
Besides, doesn't this
violate the Three Laws?
We're talkin' 'bout
Danny and Gina here.
They'll find a way to settle
this between themselves.
Forget about them,
our priority is those bodies.
C'mon, gimme a hand.
Right.
[CHAD]
Oh, and, Cody,
don't mention the Three Laws
in front of me ever again.
Don't like 'em. Never have.
[DOUG]
I don't get it.
How am I the only
one outta breath?
Somethin's off about this guy.
After all I done to him,
he's actin' like it's nothin'.
[gasps]
A freakin' overdose?
Really? The hell're
you thinkin', bro?
Don't tell me you do
this shit every time y--!
[DOUG]
Whoa!
Hold on! Wait a sec!
[DOUG]
Uh. What?
Ginger?
P-Please s-stop this.
Stop fighting im-mmediately.
[NICOLAS] This four-eyed
chick's with the Guild.
[whimpers]
Nicolas, just give it
a rest. She's here.
Now!
That's an order!
Heh. Sorry 'bout that.
Sometimes he doesn't
listen so good.
I th-think it's wise
to restrain him.
[PAULKLEE]
"Never harm a Normal.
Obey your masters.
Defend yourself."
[gasps]
Gina!
[PAULKLEE] The Four Fathers
fought tooth-and-nail
to put those Three
Laws into effect.
They did so in order to liberate
us Twilights from slavery.
And it's because of these laws
that what minimal rights
we have are guaranteed.
If you violate them,
it puts us all at risk.
All of this was drilled
into you as a child.
Yet you still don't
know when to quit.
[gunshots]
[thud]
You know Daniel Monroe's life
is protected under
the Three Laws.
Besides, his death would
upset the balance of power
in Ergastulum.
Again, things you already know.
You miserable twit!
Uh, Ms. Paulklee, ma'am, wait!
Don't you think
that's a little much?
[BOTH gasp]
[WORICK]
Nic!
You bi--!
Best not to get in
sir's way, normal.
[WORICK]
Eh... Heh.
[PAULKLEE] I'm not gonna
do anything to you, Worick.
Your man's the one
I've got business with.
We'll be done soon.
Just wait there.
[NICOLAS groaning]
[NICOLAS]
Damn it. It hurts. But how?
I should still have some time
before the Celebrer wears off.
[glass cracking]
[NICOLAS]
The fuck?
This is... a downer.
Hey, wait!
[PAULKLEE] Glad to see
you're feeling pain again.
It's my drug of choice
to make sure morons like you
can't defend themselves.
[NICOLAS] I hate fighting women
who are bigger than me.
How is it she becomes even
more imposing with age?
Haven't I warned you
about the dangers
of OD-ing on Celebrer, Nicolas?
Especially the uppers.
[PAULKLEE]
Or is that what you want?
To end up like her.
Like Veronica.
[chuckling]
[PAULKLEE]
How disappointing.
I thought you were
smarter than this.
Lookin' out for
yourself is fine.
Long as you uphold
your responsibilities
to the man with your
contract, Nicolas.
[gunshot]
[ALEX]
Damn it. Fell asleep.
Alex!
[yelps]
Come on, Nic.
Stand up straight.
Jesus. How's someone so short
weigh so damn much?
[WORICK]
Damn that old Paulklee bitch!
She knows how Nic gets when
you pump 'im with downers!
What a day.
First the police question us,
then a gang war,
you ruin my shirt,
and now it's raining.
Eh?
You what? You want your jacket?
[WORICK]
Um.
I left it behind.
Fine, I'll buy you a new one.
But you owe me a new shirt!
And that cost way more
than your stupid jacket.
So, be ready to open
your wallet, bu--!
[growls]
[WORICK]
Oh, man! Come on!
[ALEX]
It's really comin' down.
I hope the boys
are someplace dry.
[ALEX gasps]
[ALEX]
No. It's impossible.
I watched him die
right in front of me.
I shot him. I did.
Again and again and again.
It happened.
Idiot. All this and I still...?
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[NINA]
Stay safe!
[gasps]
[WORICK yelping]
[NINA screams]
Oh, guys! I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
[WORICK]
Ow.
Sorry to drop in.
Nina, dear.
Can you patch them up?
Also, do you have a phone
here I can borrow?
[NINA]
Uh...
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]