[PASSERBY A]
Hm?
Hey! Jerkass,
watch where you're--
Oh, shit! A Tag!
Uh. Hi?
[NINA]
Whoa! Um.
Wh-Who the heck are you?
Where...? Where are
Nico and Worick?
[WORICK]
Is that Nina?
Ha! I can tell that
screech anywhere.
Hey, short stuff!
Put some clothes on.
She's a little girl!
[NINA]
I'm so sorry!
No! Nina! You got it all wrong!
It's not what it looks like!
--[thud]
--[NINA grunts]
[NICOLAS]
Mmm.
[WORICK]
Uh, so, Nina.
I'd like you to meet Alex.
Kind of a long story,
but we brought her on
to answer the phone.
Yeah. I'm sorry
if I startled you.
Ah, she'll be fine. So, Ally,
I'd like you to
meet little Nina.
She's one of our regulars.
She works as a nurse
for Doctor Theo.
He's like our...
family physician.
She works harder
than most adults,
and she's good at it, too.
[ALEX]
Oh, wow.
Sorry I freaked.
I thought.
Well, I thought you were like,
you know, Worick's, um...
[NINA screams]
Nico!
[WORICK]
Oh, hey. You're back.
"While you were out,"
yeah right.
[NINA]
Come on.
You say that every time,
but then you always go buy one
especially for me, too.
Thank you.
[yelps]
[NINA]
Nico!
[WORICK]
So, Nina,
now that everyone's met,
and you've gotten your soda,
what brings ya by?
[NINA groaning]
[WORICK]
Somethin' tells me
you're not just here
to say "hello."
Wait, let me guess.
Doc pissed off the
wrong tough guy again?
If he was just a regular
gangster thug,
we probably would've
gone to Inspector Adkins
to deal with him.
Yeah, say no more.
This guy's a Tag.
[ALEX]
What is a Tag?
[NICOLAS grunts]
[NINA]
Yeah, definitely.
One of Marco's men
stopped by the clinic,
and he was no match
at all for this guy.
He said he was positive this
Tag is a B Rank or higher.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[NINA]
Oh, wait.
Hold on a sec. Nico.
[grunts]
[NINA]
The refill on your meds.
Doctor Theo prescribes 'em,
I deliver 'em.
He said your supply
should run out soon, right?
[ALEX]
Meds? For what?
[ALEX] Deafness aside,
he looks pretty healthy.
Hey, Nic. I'm gonna catch up
with you later, okay?
I got a little errand
to go run first.
[gasps]
Nico, not all at once!
It is most certainly not okay!
You have to stick to
the dosage Doc tells you!
[WORICK]
Hey, uh, Ally?
Hate to ask,
but I need a favor.
[PUNK A]
Are you sure that's the girl?
[PUNK B]
Yeah.
[PUNK C]
What about that dude she's with?
One with the sword.
Kill him, or...?
[PUNK B]
Kill him.
[ALEX]
Hey, boys.
Any a you wanna come
with me, have some fun?
Or all of you even.
I'll give you a good rate.
[PUNK A]
Tch. I don't need no whore.
Go find a street corner.
We're workin' here.
[ALEX] Discipline-play
costs extra, daddy.
I've been workin'
this spot for weeks.
Just no traffic today.
Come on. Come keep me warm.
You're so strong.
Bitch, I told ya to am-scray!
We ain't gonna say it again.
[thud]
[gasps]
[NICOLAS]
Hm?
[PUNK A]
Die, bastard!
[WORICK]
Ciao, bitch.
[NINA]
That sounded like...
[NINA] Very funny, Nico.
You don't hear anything.
[NINA] I think those
were maybe... gunshots.
[NINA] I'm sure it
was nothing. Let's go.
I bet Doctor Theo's gotten
tired of waiting for us.
[THEO] How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm not interested in
partnering with anybody.
[B/2]
Well that ain't very neighborly.
I mean, you know you're gonna
get a fat stack of bills
if you help our crew, right?
[B/2]
Seems like a waste.
Rottin' away in this run-down
hellhole of a clinic.
Treatin' nasty-ass diseases
for whatever change the street
trash can scrounge up.
Don't you think you
deserve better, Doc?
I don't really mind it.
I like my life, and the
squalor suits me fine.
Now if you'll
excuse me, I have--
This girl works
for you, don't she?
Nina, I think it is, right?
Cute little cupcake.
Can tell she gonna be a fine
piece o' ass soon. No doubt.
My boys are grabbin'
her up as we speak.
Maybe we turn her out early.
Put that ass to work for us.
Yeah, you mean her?
[PUNK G]
Hey, what's the kid doin' here?
[PUNK F]
Is that a fuckin' samurai sword?
I'm sorry to bother
you, Handyman.
Where's the other guy?
Playin' hooky today?
[whimpers]
[B/2] Hey. How the fuck
did this happen?
[PUNK F] Uh. Boss,
there's gotta be some--
I don't want excuses!
I wanna know why
you shit-for-brains
can't get even the
simplest job right!
[WORICK]
Aw, man.
Have to get Chad out here to
dispose of all this garbage.
[ALEX] How 'bout a heads-up
next time you go on a rampage?
You ruined my top.
Blood doesn't come out and
I only got like two of these.
Ah, shit. Sorry about that.
I'll buy you some new clothes
later, cool? Something nice.
Still, though,
you're takin' it well.
I mean, most chicks would
be throwin' a damn fit.
[ALEX]
"Taking it well"?
I've been sick to my
stomach ever since.
How could I just help someone
murder people like that?
[WORICK] Damn. So this
guy was a mercenary, huh?
[ALEX]
Those aren't like Nicolas'.
But Nicolas is no
ordinary mercenary, is he?
Well, I guess that would depend
on your definition
of "ordinary,"
but he's sure as
hell not like them.
Yeah, he's a former mercenary,
but he's a Tag too, see?
[B/2] Guessin' my men met
with your good graces.
Eh, Handyman?
Been hearing stories
'bout some weirdo Asian Tag
running 'round
District Eight lately,
stickin' his nose
where it don't belong.
You're shorter than
I thought you'd be.
[NICOLAS grumbles]
S'all good.
Let's do this, my brother.
My boys can thank you
after it's over.
[THEO]
He's ranked B/2, huh?
Seems I was right
to call in Nicolas.
Police wouldn't stand a chance
against a guy like him.
No specific instructions.
However you see fit.
Just don't leave too big a mess.
Hate to cause trouble
for Inspector Adkins.
And of course, make sure Nina
doesn't get so much
as a scratch on her.
Screw that part up,
I'll kill ya myself.
[B/2]
S'like a bad cliché.
Jackass brought a samurai
sword to a gunfight.
Maybe it's a trick?
Either way, dude's puny as hell.
Whatever weapon he packin',
he's still a damn Low.
Prob'ly a D Rank, max.
[B/2]
Huh?
[THEO]
Says you'll last three minutes.
Nina, come here.
[NINA]
Uh, okay.
Hey, wait a minute!
Stay put, you little brat!
[PUNKS gasp]
Let me 'splain for ya, big guy.
You certainly look
like a decent fighter,
but this guy's totally deaf,
and he still wants to
give you a handicap.
So it's safe to say he's gonna
wipe the floor with you.
[B/2]
Asshole!
[ALEX]
It's weird.
There are people around,
but we haven't actually passed
anyone directly in a while.
You're not from around
here, are you, Ally?
That obvious?
[WORICK] Mostly, I can tell
from the way you talk.
But the big giveaway is that
you don't know about Tags.
S'okay, though. I was an
outsider here once, too.
[B/2]
Three minutes, huh?
[growls]
I'll show you!
[yelling]
Boss, are you okay?
You're playin', right?
[growls]
You wanna know what's
gonna take three minutes?!
That's how long it'll take me
to turn your face into
friggin' mincemeat!
Nina.
Go inside and call Inspector
Adkins. Usual drill.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
[THEO] Wait. Crawl
through the back window.
[NINA]
What?
Side note. I seem
to 've lost my keys.
[NINA]
Eh...
[NINA] Oh, man. Nico's just
toying with that creep.
Chad's not gonna
be happy about this.
[PUNK E]
Hey! Where's the kid?
[PUNK G]
Huh?
[PUNK E]
Wait! There she is!
[PUNK G] Stop! Come
back here, you little shit!
[THEO] Sorry, my nurse
is currently occupied.
[THEO] The doctor, however,
is ready to see you.
[B/2]
Damn it!
Coward! Stand still and
fight me like a man!
[THEO]
Hey!
Hey! Handyman!
I don't mind you fighting here.
But don't let him tear up the
whole damn neighborhood.
My clinic takes any more damage,
I won't be able to--
[B2 yelling]
Ha! You snooze,
you lose your head!
[NICOLAS] That actually hurt.
Guy's damn strong.
[phone ringing]
[CODY] Central Police.
First Investigation Division.
Hold on.
Inspector Adkins, phone!
[CHAD]
Take a message.
I'm still busy cleanin'
up the mess of bodies
Worick left for
us earlier today.
Are you sure?
It's Tina, that girl nurse
from Doctor Theo's office
in District Seven.
She saying that Nicolas is
fighting another Tag there.
[CHAD]
What?
Shit!
I'm sick of those assholes
acting up without permission!
Change of plans!
We're goin' to
Doctor Theo's first.
Bring the car around front,
Cody. Go on! Hop to!
[CODY]
Right. Yes sir!
Oh, shut up.
If you'd a killed him right
away like you're capable of,
then this never
would've happened!
So now it's your turn to die!
I'm gonna saw up your body and
sell your most valuable organs!
Yeah, so, uh, Boss?
Stop fuckin' around!
I'm sick of both of you tryin'
to make a fool outta me!
Mute Asian midget and
quack-ass doctor! Come on!
[NICOLAS]
Your three minutes are up.
[B2 whimpers]
Now, if you don't mind...
...I'll take your face...
...and turn it into a pile
o' friggin' mincemeat.
[WORICK]
So yeah. Tags.
Ah, cripes. How am I
supposed to explain this?
They're like...
Well, this city's also home
to a special breed of man.
Distinct from normal folks
like you and me
in a lotta different ways.
As many ways as there
are names for 'em.
There's "Tags."
"Monsters." "Victims."
Fancy guys call 'em the
"legacy of past sins."
There's even a cult
that's sprung up
who worships 'em like gods. Heh.
They're special, all right,
but not that special.
There's a couple kinds of tags.
Toe tags on a corpse,
for instance.
Identifyin' soldiers who
got killed in battle.
But these dog tags on the
guys we're talking about,
they got a whole
different implication.
Which is?
[B2 yelling]
[WORICK] Their tags identify
them as something "other".
Acts as a warning, if you will.
[WORICK]
You know, like "Beware of dog."
[WORICK] Man, they're
really goin' at it, huh?
Yo! Nic! Nicely done!
[B2 groaning]
Ugh. Jeez. Think maybe
you took it too far?
What do we do if he kicks it?
[WORICK]
Shit.
I know you guys are built tough,
but that's a lot to
come back from.
[WORICK] He was a
B2, huh? What a waste.
Siccin' someone this high-ranked
on a nobody like the doc?
Guess one o' the families
has money to burn.
[B2 groaning]
[WORICK]
Y'know, like "Beware of dog."
[CHAD]
I've told you guys!
Don't leave me dead
or maimed bodies!
Don't damage buildings!
And if you're gonna
fight with Tags,
do it someplace I
don't have to see it!
Jesus!
Can't even clean your last mess
'fore I gotta deal with another.
Look, man. I said we were sorry.
[NICOLAS grunts]
This right here. This is
why your wife left you.
[CHAD] You leave my wife
outta this, asshole!
You want me to take you for a
nickel ride in the squad car?
[sighs]
[THEO]
Call girl, huh?
Here.
[ALEX]
Huh?
Uh. What is this?
[NINA]
Doctor Theo!
I just saw Worick and Nico.
I gave them the package
like you wanted.
[THEO]
Oh, good. Thanks, Nina.
I'm so sorry.
I wish the clinic had somewhere
more comfortable for you to sit.
But how are you feeling
now? Any better?
[ALEX]
Mmm.
Yeah, I'm fine.
But what about you?
Are you okay?
With... all of that?
I'd be lying if I said
I was totally cool.
But that's how it is here.
I'm used to it.
Oh. Well, I envy you that.
Nina, can I ask
you something?
Sure.
Aren't you afraid of
Nicolas? Even a little?
I get why you would ask that.
But you're probably just afraid
because you don't know yet.
About Twilights, I mean.
Wait, what are Twilights? I--
[WORICK]
Yo! Ally!
Hey, we should be
headin' back now.
[ALEX]
Oh, yeah.
[NINA]
Alex, wait!
Nico's, um...
Nico's not scary at all.
He's just a grumpy-butt.
All right.
We'll be in touch once we
finish with the delivery.
[NINA]
Bye, guys!
[WORICK]
Let's go, Ally.
[ALEX]
Yeah, coming.
[giggles]
[IVAN sighs]
[IVAN] So, you failed
to recruit the doctor?
Yeah. I...
[IVAN] You know, you guys really
are just useless animals.
Absolutely pathetic.
[IVAN] You can call
yourselves "Twilights"
or whatever you want,
wear these stupid collars
around your necks,
but still, you're nothing
more than garbage.
[IVAN] Ugh, he makes
me sick. Get rid of him.
[B2 whimpers]
No! Wait! Please, just
give me another shot, okay?
Listen, I swear, I'm not
gonna fail you again!
You don't even have to pay me,
all right? I'm beggin' ya!
[thud]
[IVAN]
Thanks, but no.
I got plenty more just
like you in my arsenal.
[IVAN] Ergastulum's chock
friggin' full of 'em.