I don't get it. What do you
mean you can't save him?
His injuries weren't
that serious.
[DOCTOR]
That's right.
He just has a minor infection.
For now, his life's not
in any immediate danger.
For now? But...?
[DOCTOR]
More importantly, Wallace,
have you seen your father yet?
Don't change the
subject, Doctor.
[DOCTOR]
They don't live for very long.
It happens rather frequently.
Mercenary groups
or mafia families
will often take in Twilights
and use them as slaves.
What do Twilights have to--?
You're wrong.
You're wrong!
It's not true! It can't be!
It just... I mean. I've read
all about them in my books!
Twilights are monsters!
They have huge bodies,
and they're all crazy strong!
[DOCTOR]
Wallace.
[WALLACE]
They kill without mercy.
But not Nicolas.
He's not like that!
He's not...
He's not a monster.
[DOCTOR]
Let him go.
Just accept it and let him go.
Sure, if you have money,
you can get your hands
on some Celebrer.
But you're a smart kid, Wallace,
so you must already know.
Deep down.
It's not fair to fill him with
the false hope of a long life.
Put him out of his misery.
[gasps]
[ALEX]
Uh, hey. Good morning.
Sounded like you were havin'
a bad dream, so I let myself in.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm all good now.
Thanks.
[ALEX]
Whenever I'd have a bad dream,
my mother would do this
for me and I'd feel better.
Don't know if it works
as well on grown men.
Ya know, Ally, I think
that's the first time
you've ever mentioned
your past to me.
[WORICK sighs]
[WORICK]
Hey. Remember what you asked me?
You know, if I ever really
thought about the why.
I've been askin' the same
thing since I was a kid.
Unfortunately,
the answer just never seemed
to find its way to me.
[ALEX]
And now?
Figure it out? An answer?
[NINA laughing]
[NINA]
Now go that way, Nico!
Huh? Wait, you're deaf?
You mean this whole time
I was just talking to myself?
What the fuck, man?
No wonder I couldn't
get through to you.
How was I supposed to
know your compensation
was a busted up set of ears?
[DOUG growls]
[NICOLAS]
This guy's a trip.
You never said nothing;
I just figured something
was wrong with your voice!
God damn!
[DOUG]
What is that, sign language?
Do I look like someone
who's had enough education
to understand that shit?
[NINA squeals]
[CHAD]
What're you up to now, Doug?
Hey, Nicolas.
You know each other?
It's a message from
the Mercenary Guild.
Says when you get back to base,
your ass is grounded.
I'm headed that way now. Hop in
an' I can give you a lift.
[sighs] This really sucks balls.
I got permission last year to
take my own jobs on the side,
so why are they mad?
[CHAD]
Dumbass! Why do you think?
You went after
the Monroe family!
The freaking
Monroe family!
Shit, if you'd succeeded,
the Guild woulda done a hell
of a lot more than ground you.
Huh?
Huh? Wanna know how old Doug is?
Uh, Nico, you should know.
Doug's compensation is--
I meet all of the
Guild's requirements.
They let you start freelancing
on your own once you hit 20.
I'm gonna turn 21 this year,
though I may not look it.
[NINA laughing]
Oh my gosh, Nico! I'm flying!
Oh, man. All those chopped
up bodies were Twilights?
Appreciate you puttin' a rush
on these autopsies, Theo.
I know how busy you are.
Now that I've pinned
down what they were,
have you figured out the who?
Had to bring Worick down
to the station for an assist,
but yeah, more or less.
Trouble is, since they'd
had their tags stolen,
it's just taken a hell of a lot
longer than I would've liked.
[THEO] That big guy
who was making trouble
outside my practice
the other day?
He was tossed in
with the other vics.
What? You mean he wasn't
killed with them?
[THEO]
That's how it looks anyway.
None of the other bodies
exhibited injuries
consistent with being
restrained before they died.
The rest clearly fought back.
More time, and I might've
gotten better details.
Huh?
[THEO] All of 'em, though, were
pretty much in their primes.
Well, as far as Twilights go.
Now, if they'd been drugged or
somethin', that'd explain a lot.
But then they wouldn't have
these defensive wounds.
Judging from the cuts,
there was an active struggle
and they got dismembered
while still alive.
Corsicans only
work with Normals.
You really think they could
take out Twilights like this?
Oh, wow.
I was certain that was
your doing with the sword.
That pile of District
Six bodies-- Huh?
Um, Doug, Nico wants to know
why you took the Monroe job
without the Guild's okay.
I don't know. No reason.
Just because Gunslinger
Danny's a big shot boss.
Figured if I started
something with that guy,
I'd get to battle some
high-category bodyguards.
Little did I know the only
Tag Danny keeps under him
is some weak-ass Low.
Man, I can't live every
moment of my short life
thinkin' about those
three dumb laws.
Not exactly like I'm a member
of the Paulklee Guild by choice.
The truth is, I
could never figure out
all the unwritten rules you
got in this ghetto-ass town.
So wait, you're not
originally from here?
[DOUG]
South Gate was my home.
Got committed to
Ergastulum when I was 16
and drafted to the Guild.
What's wrong? Don't meet
a lotta rogue Tags?
What? West Gate?
You, too?
What's the matter, Doug?
Usually, I can't get you
to shut up if I try.
[DOUG] Yo, Pops, if you got
any work you're sendin' my way,
make sure I don't run
into him, all right?
Well, this is
an unexpected turn.
You really don't wanna have to
tango with Nic again, do you?
[DOUG] Until today, I've never
met a West Gate survivor.
I see. Pining for the
outside world, are ya?
[DOUG]
No. No, it ain't that.
[RADIO] With resistance
from anti-Twilight factions
continuing, the government
has again ordered
the mobilization
of mercenary units.
This move comes in tandem
with new, mandated curfews
for neighboring districts.
[NICOLAS]
Cap-- Uh. Captain!
[GASTON] Can't have any
dead weight in my unit.
If your symptoms
have gotten that bad,
it's not even worth
tryin' to sell you off.
F-Fath-- Father!
Don't pretend you're human.
You little freak.
Nicolas! Hey! Nic!
Nic, it's all right.
I figured everything out.
You don't have to
serve him anymore.
When I...
When I showed him the cash,
he was glad to sell you to me.
Look, I even got your own
Celebrer supply from the doc.
You'll be fine.
So, let's...
Nic, what's wrong?
[ALEX]
Nicolas?
I, um, brought you
a change of clothes.
[ALEX]
How you feelin'? Better?
[PAULKLEE]
This time, there were 12 bodies.
Autopsies haven't
been performed yet,
but I think it's safe to assume
they're all Twilights, correct?
Well that would be
music to my goddamn ears.
Saves me the trouble of
dealing with you directly.
Listen, Mr. Corsica.
We all know that most likely
it was your clan who did this.
Ma'am, I--
[LORETTA]
Would you destroy the balance
my father and his crew forged?
You claim to despise them.
But I think you're
hiring Twilights
whenever it's
convenient for you!
Cut the bullshit!
I've had enough!
You actually think I
would hire a Twilight?
That I would ever get in bed
with those sick freaks?
The thought alone makes me sick!
I would rather have one of
your men chop off my head
with a dull knife and shit
down my bloody neck hole
than associate with those
filthy Twilight scum!
What kind of hypocrite
do you take me for?
Stop talking out your
ass, you little twat!
You filthy old bastard!
She's the damn head
of our family now!
Show some fuckin' respect.
--Calm down, Galahad.
--Asshole!
Now, now. Let's all
take a breath.
Bickerin' with each other won't
solve any of our problems.
True, this appears to
have been a massacre
only a Twilight
coulda pulled off.
But that doesn't necessarily
implicate any of us
or suggest anyone here
had any involvement.
So an outsider?
Are you implying the
government was behind this?
I'm just sayin' we shouldn't
jump to conclusions is all.
This town is crawlin' with
miscreants and lowlifes,
so you just never know.
Don't you agree?
[THEO]
So tell me.
How's your memory been
the last few days?
Has it been fuzzy
or had any gaps?
Have you lost your
sense of time at all?
[ALEX]
No.
[THEO] And what about Barry?
Still seeing him?
Uh, no, I... Not even once.
Then you're making
good progress.
I'd like you to keep
on takin' those pills,
just to be on the safe side.
Also, I understand
you're a prostitute.
I'm not judgin' or anything,
but you should be aware
that excessive stress
can make it more likely
for your hallucinations
and anxiety to return.
So try not to get in
over your head.
That's it. We're all done here.
I'll put the bill on
the Handymen's tab.
[ALEX]
Uh. Doctor.
Yeah, what?
[ALEX] Well. Um.
About your arm. I, uh--
[THEO]
Can you make sweets?
[ALEX] Well, I guess I can
manage something simple.
[THEO] If ya wanna apologize,
come whip up somethin' sometime.
Nina'd be thrilled.
[ALEX]
Okay then, I'd love to.
Thank you for waiting for me.
[ALEX]
So I was wondering.
Can I stay with you
a little while longer?
I still haven't found
another place,
but I'll get outta your
hair soon as possible.
Please, Nic.
[NICOLAS]
Dummy.
[ALEX]
Huh?
[NICOLAS] Your sign language
is all screwed up.
I don't understand you.
Start over.
In that book.
And don't be so rough with it.
I only have the one copy.
He caught me smokin' these.
Next time he catches me with
a cigarette, he might kill me.
Hey, so how are you
startin' to fit in now?
With that new mercenary squad?
North Gate, weren't they?
Right.
What a joke.
Nothing's changed, has it?
For real though.
I'm sick of this shit.
[NICOLAS]
K-Kill?
[inaudible]
[WALLACE screams]
[WALLACE]
Dad.
Dad!
[WALLACE] I'm sorry.
It wasn't me. I swear!
Please believe me.
I never wanted this.
No!
[WALLACE'S BROTHER whimpering]
--[thud]
--[cat meows]
[thud]
Nico...
What... have you done?
Oh God... Nic!
[inaudible]
[WALLACE yells]
[WALLACE] Oh, no!
You don't get to do that.
There's no way I'm
letting you do that.
Not after what you've done.
I'm not going to
let you die today, Nic.
You don't get to take
the easy way out.
Yours will be slow.
Nothing like theirs was.
You'll know a lifetime of pain.
Years and years
of real suffering...
...before you get
the privilege to die!
That's an order, Nic!
Obey your master!
[NICOLAS]
Don't need that anymore.
Have to pull it out.
[WALLACE screams]
[NICOLAS]
Wallace.
[DELICO]
Worick.
[WORICK] Hey, how come
Yang-Yang's not with ya?
[DELICO]
Four Fathers' meeting.
Only Twilights allowed are the
ones ranked "capo" or above.
That'd explain it.
Sucks gettin' left out, huh?
[DELICO] Thanks, but why
aren't you or Nic there?
You've been escortin'
the boss around, right?
Speakin' of, where is Nic?
[WORICK]
Ah, you know how it is.
We'll always be
considered outsiders.
'Sides, if I had brought Nic,
he'd be in the same boat as
you, Delly. Stuck out here.
[DELICO] You're pretty
calm about all this.
Someone's huntin' Tags.
Even the high-ranked
ones are goin' down.
Chances are,
Nic'd be no exception.
I mean, the poor guy's
on his own.
You're his only contract holder,
and he's got no
syndicate behind him.
Somethin' happens to him,
what happens to you?
[WORICK]
It's okay.
[DELICO]
Hm?
It's okay. I bet
my father will be happy.
Don't you worry 'bout him.
He buys the farm,
it was meant to be.
One less thing tyin' me down.
Fact, I'll probably
end up happier for it.
[WALLACE] But it's not enough.
In fact, it's not even close.
That's why I'm thinkin'
everyone else should die, too.
You mean that? Dude.
Sure, deep inside, I despise
Tags. Think they're monsters.
That's fine, I hate
all you Normals, too.
Aw, come on, Delly,
I'm just yankin' your chain.
You gotta lighten up there.
Maybe I will if ya
stop callin' me "Delly."
[WALLACE]
Nicolas... why?
Why don't you ever
wonder... "why?"
Figure it out? An answer?
[WORICK] I don't think
there is an answer.
[WORICK] If there was,
it'd be all over, right?
[TWILIGHT screaming]
Erica, I wanna take this.
[ERICA] No, Mikhail.
We only take the tags.
[MIKHAIL]
Aww.
[TWILIGHT groaning]
[TWILIGHT]
Have mercy. Please.
Y'brought this on
yourself, mister!
'Cause you did your friends
wrong, they abandoned you.
[ERICA]
We're done.
Okay!
What's wrong? Nicolas, what's--?
[ALEX]
Nicolas?