[PUNK C] Uranos, he-he doesn't
even want Monroe's head!
He's after what Monroe protects.
The Cristiano family!
The Cristianos, huh?
I heard their only
business now's drugs.
The Corsicans have
their own drug trade.
What's their angle?
[PUNK C] I... I don't
know their reasons!
All I know's what I overheard
the Corsican capos sayin'!
[WORICK] You work for a
Twilight-hater like Uranos
and thought it wise to
go off and hire that runt?
Poor guy.
It won't do any good to
send you back to them alive.
You're just a pawn who
served his purpose.
[MONROE]
I reached out to Chad,
made sure all their remains
got returned to us.
The funeral's tomorrow.
[DELICO]
I'm sorry, sir.
Yang.
Did you patch up Delico again?
Didn't I specifically tell you
to take him to Doc Theo's?
[YANG]
Uh!
Yes, but, sir, he told
me that he was--
The wound was hardly
life threatening.
I told Yang to go ahead
and stitch me up.
No use wasting the
doctor's time over it.
[sighs]
[MONROE] I know you're
tryin' to play it safe.
And I know there's
bad blood lingerin'
from the slavery days,
but you're people,
built a little tougher than
usual, but still people.
You're my shield.
Ya can't be takin'
shortcuts with your health.
I'd prefer to die a quiet,
boring death as
a senile old man.
And so...
...that means I need my shield
to be damn near indestructible.
I plan on hangin' onto ya
for as long as I possibly can.
[MILES]
Might wanna tone down
the "caring father figure"
routine, boss.
There's bound to be some
youngsters in the family
who get jealous if
they feel they don't get
the same attention.
And where the hell did
"Gunslinger Danny" go?
His name alone used to make
enemies piss their pants.
That's just rude.
People still fear me, right?
[MILES]
It's more like...
...they're afraid of you
squeezing their cheeks.
[MILES]
If the Handyman's right,
and the Corsicans really
are trying to muscle in
on our Cristiano business,
an all-out gang war in the
city will erupt, won't it?
That's a good question.
But this is Ergastulum.
An' considerin'
what I saw today,
it's the only way things can go.
[IVAN] Treatin' even foot
soldier scum like family.
It's giving me heartburn.
I know you feel the same way.
[CORSICA]
Why is Monroe still alive?
No one told me it
was gettin' jobbed out
to that dreadlocked
Twilight kid.
I panicked. Damn near
got killed myself.
[CORSICA] The Twilight's hiring
is on me. I'll deal with that.
I'd heard that the only
Twilight Monroe has
is some bullshit D/0.
Seems they hired
extra help, too.
[CORSICA] If you can, search out
their help, and eliminate them.
Yes, sir. Will do.
[CORSICA] Oh, and about those
bodies in the factory.
The old detective linking me
to them would be troublesome.
[IVAN] Don't worry, I got
a cop friend on the take.
Same office as that
old shriveled ol' Dick.
I'll make sure the
investigation goes nowhere fast.
[IVAN]
Hmph.
[GASTON]
Those are expensive.
Don't waste 'em.
[MERCENARY A]
Your kid always listens.
[GASTON]
He better pay attention.
The dose I give him
is typically just enough
not trigger an attack.
[MERCENARY B]
He needs that much to walk.
Forget being able to
run away from this place.
And if somehow he did bolt, he
wouldn't last long without it.
He knows the key to living
any kind of life at all
is to just keep quiet and
do what the humans tell ya.
But, at best, we're
still talking about a life
that croaks in its mid-30s.
Why's a Twilight in our
unit in the first place?
[GASTON] Junkie whore I
knocked up had no business
raising a baby addict.
Figured if I could keep him
alive until he's in demand,
I could sell him
off in Ergastulum
and make a nice chunk of change.
So what happened
to your son's mom?
[GASTON]
Killed her.
[phone ringing]
[WORICK]
Ally's not pickin' up.
Hm?
Hold it there, Worick!
You can't smoke that in here.
We've got patients!
AW, come on, kid.
Just this one?
Yeah, no. But here,
make do with this.
So, uh, our boy Nic's
gonna pull through, right?
There won't be any permanent
nerve damage, fortunately.
And no broken bones
where he got shot.
Once his wounds heal, he'll
be all set to go back to work.
Damn straight. He's the
toughest bastard I know.
[NINA] Still, I doubt he'll
be able to walk right away.
[WORICK]
Hm?
[NINA]
The downers she shot him with
were triple the normal strength.
[WORICK]
Wait, triple?
I don't understand.
I thought the legal limit
was only one-and-a-half
times the regular dose.
[NINA]
Yes, but Gina's are custom-made.
And that crazy
little runt there,
she hit his kid-size ass
with four of those things?
[NINA] He's got a high
tolerance for downers.
Some people, like Nico,
are more susceptible
to the drug's effects
and get totally knocked out
after just a single dose,
but Doug there's the opposite.
Takes a lot for it to
have any effect at all.
Fortunately, it was only
Celebrer he got shot with.
Those just pierce
the skin a little,
so even I was able to treat him
and patch up his injuries.
If they'd have been
regular bullets,
then Doctor Theo would've
had to extract them.
[gasps]
Uh, Worick?
Oh, sorry, I was just thinkin'
how awesome you are.
You study hard, got
both feet on the ground.
Gonna make a hell of a doctor
someday. An' I mean that.
Thank you.
[WORICK sneezes, groans]
Oh, you poor guy! I'll go make
something to warm you up.
[WALLACE]
Well? Didja learn it?
Simple, right? Now
communicating should be...
When you're with me, you
can just act normally, cool?
And when you're with me,
sit in the chair.
Understand?
[WALLACE] It's like trying
to talk to an animal.
Or a machine.
Like he's... not really
a person somehow.
Is it that Twilights aren't?
[WALLACE]
No, of course not.
Hey, what happened to your arm?
That bruise wasn't
there yesterday.
[NICOLAS]
I... I fell down.
[WALLACE]
Me too. I fall down a lot.
[DOMENICO] What's all that
commotion out there?
[MAID A] A-Apparently a
riot's broken out nearby.
[DOMENICO] Those anti-Twilight
protestors again?
Get Michel and my wife
to a safe room.
[MAID A] Yes, sir. And what
about Master Wallace?
[DOMENICO]
Leave him.
[clatter]
[gasps]
What?! Are you nuts?!
[DOMENICO] Not only did
you allow an intruder
onto the Arcangelo estate,
but then you stain my lawn?
[GASTON]
I'm very sorry, sir.
Don't worry, I'll give him
a stern talkin'-to.
[DOMENICO growls]
[gasps]
[thud]
[DOMENICO] What was your plan?
What were you thinking?
That you'd ingratiate
yourself to me?
[DOMENICO] No, you thought
you could tame that boy
and then sic him
on me, is that it?
Was this just a
practice run? Was it?
No, Dad, I swear! I-I didn't
do anything! Dad, please!
[DOMENICO] Don't grovel like
your slut of a mother did,
you miserable little curse!
[WORICK]
Now that I think about it,
how'd you know we were coming?
[NINA]
What?
You were "Jenny-on-the-spot"
with your first aid kit.
Oh, uh...
I heard you talking?
Outside, in that downpour?
[NINA] Well, I've always
had great hearing, and--
[sneezes]
Jeez, kid, are you okay?
I'm fine.
As I was saying, I can
always tell your voice.
But just yours, Worick.
[WORICK] Aw, man.
Am I really that loud?
Guess I oughtta be more careful.
[WORICK]
Nic? Hey.
How you feel, buddy?
Yeah, I know, like crap.
I'm gonna pop back
over to the office.
What? Oh, a change o' clothes?
Yeah, fine. I'll bring
somethin' by later.
Hey.
Don't make me do that anymore.
Use that word "order"
on a Twilight.
[WORICK]
Here's the deal.
Corsica's on the move.
He's after the Cristianos,
which of course
upsets the balance.
The vics from that body-dumping
case Chad hauled us in for?
[WORICK]
They were all Tags.
One of 'em was even that B/2
you beat up outside Doc Theo's.
[WORICK] Don't know what his
connection to Corsica was,
but it's clear he was involved
in somethin' bigger.
However this shakes out,
the linchpin is Mr. Monroe,
savior of the Twilights.
And the man who's
currently got the Cristianos
under his umbrella.
[WORICK]
I owe him too much.
It's why I can't let anything
happen to the Monroes.
You're with me, right? Partner?
[MIKHAIL laughing]
[AIDE A]
Are you sure about this?
[CORSICA]
Of course I'm sure.
I'll be in a bad
mood if he lives.
[MIKHAIL laughing]
[CORSICA] We must make
an example of that punk,
so all who work for us
know they can never hire
Twilights in Corsica's name.
[WALLACE]
I'm beat.
Sign language?
[MERCENARY B]
What do we do?
[GASTON]
Get the injector! Hurry!
[MERCENARY A]
Yes, sir!
[GASTON] Don't let him pass out.
It'll make things worse.
[MERCENARY A]
Hey! Nicky, wake up!
[MERCENARY B] We can't let
anyone see him like this!
[MERCENARY A]
Let's get him on his feet.
[WORICK]
Odd.
Don't normally see fancy black
cars passin' through here.
[NICOLAS]
I've said it for years.
It's no use. It was
always gonna end this way.
[NICOLAS] No matter how hard
they try to help us,
we're just not gonna make it.
Nicolas.
Doesn't it bother you?
If I were you,
I would run away.
Come on.
Doesn't it make you wanna
just punch the wall?
[WALLACE]
Don't you ever ask... "why?"
[chuckles]
[WALLACE]
That's sloppy.
[WALLACE laughing]
[FEMALE RADIO VOICE A] Riots led
by anti-Twilight factions
at the four gates surrounding
Ergastulum have escalated,
and the Twilight hunts that
accompany them are on the rise.
The government has called
in mercenary forces
from all over to bring the
situation under control.
[RIOTERS shouting]
[MERCENARY B] Damn it!
There's too many of 'em!
We can't break through!
Everyone, fall back!
Fall back, now!
[WORICK] Damn!
Freezin' my nuts off out here!
[WORICK]
She with a client?
Hey. Ally! I'm ho--
[THEO]
I, uh, helped myself.
She bit me. Scratched me, too.
Looks sweet enough,
but that stray you took in
has a violent streak.
If you're gonna keep her,
you might wanna try
housebreakin' her.
Doc Theo?
[THEO]
After everything you said,
I thought I should probably
drop by and check in on her.
[THEO]
The symptoms you told me about.
Seeming distant,
like she's got cobwebs
clouding her brain.
Fuzzy memories.
Having trouble sleeping.
Those are all textbook
side effects
of the pills pimps use to keep
their women... complacent.
On the street,
they're called "TBs".
Figured you'd already
know all about 'em,
but I guess not, huh?
Good news is, even though
they're long-acting,
there's hardly any
toxicity to 'em
and they're not
particularly addictive.
Bad news is there's
a high suicide rate.
As the effects wear off,
there are intense hallucinations
that can drive them to it.
As a coping mechanism,
they often cling desperately
to their surroundings
or to objects that
have been given to them.
Even if those things are
utterly meaningless.
[WORICK]
I got careless.
Thought she was
doing better lately.
Where is she?
Ally, thank God!
Did you have a customer?
[WORICK] Let's get
you back to the office.
C'mon, you're gonna
catch a cold like tha--
Whoa, hold on!
Stop it! Stop!
Ally! It's me! Knock it off!
Ally!
[ALEX]
No, Barry.
Please don't hit me.
I'll do it. I will. Please.
Alex, hey!
[ALEX]
Worick.
B-Barry's right there.
He's always right there.
I know he's dead, but...
No, I-I have to go.
If I don't, then h-he's gonna.
[ALEX]
Oh my gosh, Worick!
I'm sorry! I have a,
uh, really hard head.
So, listen.
When you're alone with a guy,
he doesn't like hearin'
another man's name.
'Sides, who do you
think killed him?
[WORICK]
Heh.
I don't know about you,
Ally, but I am beat.
Man, I am tellin' ya.
Nothin' went right for me today.
Put in cuffs, job goes
sideways, then it rains,
and to top it off,
Nic ruined my favorite shirt.
Total shit show of a day.
But hey, I did get to touch
your sweet behind again,
so I guess I'm
all right now. Heh.
[ALEX]
Jackass.
[NICOLAS]
Master Wallace.
I'm awfully sorry.
[NICOLAS]
I messed it up.
Great. Well now what?
Only had the one
copy, you dummy.
What happened?
How did you hurt your face?
[WALLACE]
I fell down.