[WALLACE whimpering]
[WALLACE]
Dad. No.
[WORICK] Fuckin' dream.
Fuckin' memories.
Paradise, is it?
[ALEX]
Huh, he's got a tribal tattoo.
You going somewhere, Nicolas?
[ALEX]
Maybe he couldn't read my lips?
[door opens]
[WORICK]
Mornin'.
Oh, hey, Nic, you're here early.
Not my fault you get up
at dawn like an old man.
What's next, dinner at
four in the afternoon?
Uh. Ah, shit.
We got deliveries for
the god-uncle today, huh?
[WORICK]
Oh. Right. Friday.
Ally, hate to ask ya, but can
you maybe give Nic a hand?
We've got a bunch of drop-offs
to make for Doctor Theo today.
[ALEX]
Uh, sure.
But wait, don't you need me
to cover the phones?
[WORICK]
Nah, I got a job later.
If a woman answers,
it'd be... problematic.
What? You have another
job besides this?
Well, yeah.
In fact, I'd say it's
my main one, actually.
Hmm.
Hey, Nic, you seen
my good shirt?
[WORICK growls]
[WORICK]
Aw, c'mon, dude, not again.
Quit jackin' my clothes
n' shit without asking.
Huh? Whadda ya mean,
"I'm one to talk"?
Right. Yeah, well,
ya got me there.
Sorry, Master Nic.
I guess I "borrowed" your crap
without permission too.
Cool. I'll catch up to
you sometime after noon.
[ALEX]
Oh. Guess, that's my cue.
Hey, while you're out,
can pick me up some smokes?
This oughta cover it.
Wait. Eh? Oh, fine.
[ALEX] So, um, Nicolas,
can I ask you something?
This other job that Worick
has outside of the Handymen,
what is it?
[ALEX] Maybe if I could
sign it, he'd answer me.
Gigolo.
[ALEX]
Huh?
[phone rings]
[WORICK]
Hello. Thank you for calling.
You've reached the Handymen.
[WORICK]
It's been a while, Madame.
How's your husband?
[laughs]
[WORICK]
Ah.
So then, how much is
my body worth to you today?
A lot, I hope.
What're you up to, Handyman?
Walking in broad
daylight with a whore.
She give you a good price?
How many times I gotta tell ya?
I don't read hands!
And I know you can
speak at least a little.
So go on, use your words!
She's my woman now.
So don't be so hard
on her, Granny.
Ah, so that's how it is.
[ALEX]
No. Uh. Hey, wait for me!
[JOEL]
Must be rough for you, too.
Havin' to indulge him like this.
[ALEX]
Uh. Huh?
Sorry. What do you mean by that?
[ALEX]
Hey! Wait up!
[NICOLAS grunts]
[ALEX]
"Wait here."
Don't need to know sign
language to get that.
[ALEX] I forgot to ask Worick
what brand he smokes.
What do I do?
[JOEL] You're on an errand
for Worick, right?
You can stop worryin' that
pretty little face of yours.
I gotcha.
Don't know why, but
these cheap-ass things
are all the one-eyed
bastard ever smokes.
[ALEX]
So, what Nicolas just said...
[JOEL] Worick can't
do what it is he does
if someone like you is hangin'
around their place all day.
[ALEX]
Huh?
It's simple.
For as long as I can
remember with those two,
any time he has genuine
feelings for a lady,
he says she's the Tag's girl,
so his clients don't get
all bent outta shape.
[JOEL] And that, my dear, is
exactly what's happened to you.
[growls]
[gasps]
[ALEX]
Is that--?
Oh yeah, that old mess.
Time flies, don't it?
Hard to believe
it's been so long.
Read up.
[ALEX]
This boy.
"Twenty-two years have passed
since the shocking Arcangelo
murder-kidnapping
and the case remains unsolved.
After killing family
patriarch Domenico,
his wife Clarissa,
and their oldest son,
the unknown assailant
took the couple's
then 13-year-old younger son
hostage and disappeared.
Police still believe the
crimes were carried out
by a young mercenary previously
in the family's employ."
[JOEL] Everyone in town's
at least vaguely aware
of the story.
But I guess that's just
because Ergastulum
is the type of place that
attracts a certain type of man.
Wouldn't be the least bit
surprised if those boys
had fled here and
started over themselves.
But if I were you, missy,
I wouldn't be rushin'
to put down roots.
And certainly not with that Tag.
[MADAME]
You okay? Does your eye hurt?
[WORICK grunts]
[WORICK] Nah, just feels
a bit wonky, today's all.
I got painkillers if you want.
[WORICK]
Mm. No, I'm fine, babe.
[WORICK] Maybe it's just
the time of year.
[MADAME] They do say
changes in the weather
can cause old
wounds to flare up.
[WORICK]
Yeah. On rainy days it gets--
Well then, feel better?
[WORICK]
Much, actually.
[yelps]
Whoa, easy.
[MADAME chuckles]
There was a picture of a boy
in this morning's paper.
I swear he has your exact
same hair. It's eerie.
He's probably only 12 or 13,
but he reminded me of you.
[WORICK] The kid from
that old murder case?
Yeah, that's the one.
How'd you know?
[WORICK] I get it more
often than you'd think.
But then, I am pretty
boyish and adorable.
[MADAME chuckles]
[MADAME]
You goof.
[ALEX]
Uh. Nicolas. Should I just--?
Hey, so, you should bring
your friend along next time.
You know, the brooding
one with the bum ears.
The more the merrier, right?
Not gonna happen.
He's got his plate more than
full with Handymen work.
Aw, no fair.
[WORICK] My partner ain't
a gigolo, you stupid skank.
So, uh, where next?
[inaudible]
Wori--!
Bye, hon. When can
I see you again?
Who knows?
When the cash calls, I'll come.
[ALEX] You always take
the back alleys, don't you?
How come?
The main roads would
be a whole lot faster.
They would.
You'll figure out why though.
What's that mean?
[WORICK] Hell of a mess
last time, eh, Marco?
So, your boys recovered yet?
[MARCO]
Hm?
Oh, right. You mean that
business at Theo's clinic.
Luckily, all my guys are
back on their feet again.
[MARCO] What happened
afterwards? To that B/2 dude?
Beats me. I didn't ask.
Remember,
collection's next week.
You know the drill by now.
[MARCO]
Hey, yeah.
Almost forgot,
boss wanted me to invite you
to his shindig next week.
Ha. Already?
Damn, Mister Cristiano loves
his parties, doesn't he?
He'd love it if you could join.
[WORICK]
Sure, we'll be there.
Not gonna say no to a good time.
'Sides, we wanna stay
tight with you guys.
[MARCO]
Likewise.
[gunfire]
Somebody screwed up.
Ah, these goddamn kids today.
Someone throws 'em a little
cash and they flip sides.
Friggin' disgrace.
[ALEX]
His face...
So, you guys got our package?
Yeah. Here's your drugs.
Convenient for us, meeting
in a back alley, Mister Monroe.
[MONROE]
I'm hearin' things, Worick.
They're sayin' you and your
Tag pal went nuts again.
[WORICK] W-- Hey,
I had nothing to do with it.
That was all Nic.
[MONROE] You're still
the boss, are you not?
Falls on you to keep our boy
there on a tight leash.
Tch. Thanks, "Dad." Why you
always takin' his side?
Nicolas, can I have
a quick word?
[MONROE] There's something
I need to ask ya.
Tell me.
Don'tcha think it's time you
came back to the family?
We value your formidable
skills and expertise.
And believe me, the capos
would be over the moon.
Of course, you're free
to bring Worick along.
Don't even care that he's
a dirty, dirty man-whore.
Look, I'm not tryin'
to pressure ya.
Just consider it
with an open mind.
[NICOLAS]
Mister Monroe.
I would be honored
to work for you.
[NICOLAS] But I'm more
comfortable in this job
than I was before,
and I like it better, so...
I'm sorry.
Ah, I see.
That's unfortunate.
[ALL chuckle]
[PROSTITUTE A] Well, if it ain't
Worick. Long time no see.
[PROSTITUTE B]
Look at that hair.
[PROSTITUTE D]
We miss you, sugar.
You haven't been
around much lately.
[WORICK]
Yeah, I know.
And as much as I'd love
to stick around and play,
today I'm here on business.
Sorry, girls.
[PROSTITUTES chattering]
[WORICK]
Is Big Mama in?
[PROSTITUTE E] Yeah, she's here.
Just a minute, okay?
[WORICK]
Thanks, sweetie.
[ALEX]
You're popular.
Huh?
Oh. That's because
I used to work here.
We all go way back.
Still gotta come by sometimes
for the other job, though.
[ALEX] You don't sound
too pleased about it.
Yeah, no. It's a
long story. Too long.
Nicolas? You comin'?
Seriously?
Worick, don't tell me
you're still running around
with that creepy Tag?
Jesus, just ditch
the freak already.
I mean, you can't even
walk down the main roads
if you're with him, can you?
Hey! Watch it!
Well, either way,
he's prob'ly just gonna croak
like the rest of those nutj--
[WORICK] You ever open that
nasty whore mouth of yours
in front of me again...
...and I'll add another gaping
hole between your thighs.
So, unless that's what
you want, shut the fuck up.
[NICOLAS]
That dumbass.
And he's always tellin'
me not to make trouble.
[BIG MAMA]
It appears one of my girls
has been less than
courteous to you.
Handyman.
[WORICK]
Big Mama.
The usual drop-off? Come on in.
[BIG MAMA] My, my, what a
pretty girl. She a new recruit?
Ah, Nicolas. Why are
you waiting out here?
Let me see that
beautiful face of yours.
[BIG MAMA]
Sorry about that, Worick.
This place is a
Corsican shop now.
You know how they feel
about the threat
posed by Twilights.
Bordellos will attract
men like Nic.
Twilights are basically junkies,
but their drug-induced ailments
are most dangerous to others.
In this town,
everything's business
and people only care
about what's best
for their bottom line.
[ALEX]
Ailments?
[WORICK]
Big Mama.
[BIG MAMA]
Hm?
[WORICK]
Um.
Do you mind apologizing to
that one call girl for me?
I was maybe a little
too hard on her.
[BIG MAMA]
Don't worry about it.
After all, she's a whore.
She's heard far worse.
Now give me my package.
I'm a busy woman.
[WORICK]
Right. It's all here.
Special delivery from
Doc Theo's office.
Refills of the Twilight
drug, Celebrer.
Three orders of uppers
and... seven?
Seven orders of downers?
Aw, jeez. Is she
really doin' that bad?
[BIG MAMA]
She's gotten so weak.
I'm afraid she can't even move
around anymore on her own.
On her good days, we're
lucky if she eats one meal.
She doesn't feel
much pain, at least.
Much of anything, really.
Her senses are going.
I don't think she's
got much longer, hon.
[WORICK] Well, a gigolo's
job is never done.
Ally, head back to
our place with Nicolas.
[ALEX]
Uh. Huh?
Worick, you dummy.
I still have so many questions.
Sorry, girls, I'm busy.
[PROSTITUTE F] You can bring
one of my friends, too.
[ALEX]
Where is Nicolas?
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Hey, Worick. Get back okay?
[breathing deeply]
[ALEX] Those long eyelashes.
They go with his hair.
Y'know, when he's
quiet like this,
he's kind of a leading man type.
[WORICK grunts]
[gasps]
[JOEL]
Everyone in town's at least
vaguely aware of the story.
[JOEL]
But if I were you, missy,
I wouldn't be rushin'
to put down roots.
[WORICK]
She left, huh?
Hm?
Oh, Alex.
[ALEX humming]
[humming continues]
Ergastulum's a far cry
from paradise.
[ALEX]
Huh?
If ya stay in this
town too long,
you'll never friggin' escape.
It happened to me and Nic.
[WORICK]
Word to the wise. Get out now.
Only a matter of time before
you get sucked in too deep.
[ALEX]
Uh.
How long have you been a gigolo?
[WORICK]
Huh?
Jeez, how long has it been?
I guess not long after I arrived
with Nic. I woulda been... 13.
Yeah, 'bout a year after that,
Big Mama saw my potential
and brought me on.
I mean, just look at me, right?
And if you think I'm hot now,
you shoulda seen me
when I was younger.
I still got it, though.
[ALEX] Have you ever thought
about why, though?
[WORICK] Why would you ask
something like that?
[WORICK]
Huh...
But yeah...
[WORICK]
It's a damn good question.
[NICOLAS grunts]
[WALLACE screams]