[RADIO]
And in crime news,
Ergastulum police are still
investigating the gruesome
early morning discovery of
several decomposing bodies
in an abandoned
District Six factory.
In a brief press release,
authorities revealed
that many of the remains
appear to be dismembered
by a bladed weapon, only adding
to the difficulties they face
in identifying the victims,
let alone a suspect.
Up next, stay tuned for sports
and weather, after this.
[phone ringing]
[DETECTIVE A]
Yeah, Central Police.
[DETECTIVE B]
Hey, didja hear?
Chad hauled in the Handymen
for questioning.
[DETECTIVE C]
What? Aw, crap.
Well, I just hope they don't
break anything valuable,
like last time.
It's the one in there
who gives me the creeps.
How's Adkins put up
with those pricks?
So let me try to explain
this to you again, Nic.
We found a bunch of chopped up
bodies in District Six.
Now all the cuts
are really clean...
[NICOLAS] Can never remember
this police turd's name.
Hey, Nicolas.
Are you hearing me?
I mean, are you seeing?
Ah, jeez. I know you're bored,
but this is important.
[CODY]
Nicolas!
Now you're ignoring
me on purpose!
You're a right bastard
sometimes, Chad.
You know Nic won't listen
to anyone but you.
Yeah, that's the point.
[CHAD]
I turned 56 this year.
[WORICK] What? You're playin'
the "old man card" now?
[CHAD]
Fuck off.
You and Nic are on the
downslope to 40 yourselves.
You're gettin' older not cooler.
[sighs] We're gettin' old?
Guess we have been doing
"unsavory work" together
for a while.
[knocking]
No way!
[chuckles]
How old are we on these posters?
Huh? Only 17?
Damn, Nic, you haven't aged
a day since this was taken.
It's your half-Asian blood.
It's so not fair.
It makes me sick.
[CHAD]
It ain't just Nicolas.
Neither of these
meatheads ever change.
[WALLACE]
Chad... I...
Help me. I don't know
what to do anymore.
[WALLACE crying]
Yeah, go throw those things out.
[CHAD] Well, maybe they
have changed. We all have.
[WORICK]
Oh yeah?
Why then, Chad, do you
have us shackled up
like we're some
common street thugs?
What's this really about?
[sighs]
We found this today
in an abandoned factory
in District Six.
[CHAD]
Don't give me the stink eye.
I don't suspect
you guys on this,
but if I don't at least bring
ya in, they'll ride my ass.
Ain't many guys around
who can handle a weapon
like that, right?
[WORICK] Yeah, most of
these cuts came from
a real sharp blade.
Damage to the bodies is so bad,
ID-ing the victims
is going nowhere.
[CHAD] Then we agree
on a trade for your...
..."storage" skill.
[sighs]
[WORICK] See this is why
I don't trust cops.
Your work's even
dirtier than mine.
[CHAD] It'd take the boys
in the crime lab forever
to figure this one out.
Cody, it's me, let's switch.
Show Worick everything we've
got on these factory bodies,
all right?
[CODY]
Eh.
Everything?
[ALEX]
I hope that guy's all right.
It sounded pretty urgent.
[JOEL]
But if I were you, missy,
I wouldn't be rushin'
to put down roots.
And certainly not with that Tag.
I remember the last girl
they had crashin' with them.
Poor thing nearly got
killed for her troubles.
[ALEX] I'll return this, tell
'em thanks for everything...
...and then I'll leave.
Find a new job, a new place.
[BARRY]
Oh, wow.
Please don't tell me
you're givin' serious thought
to goin' back to that, Alex.
You have to've realized
the truth by now.
You are who you are and you'll
stay that way till you die.
So embrace it!
Spread your legs for those
two like you did for me.
Trade that sweet candy for rent
and I'm sure they'll let you
stay here as long as you like.
[ALEX]
Stop it, Barry!
[crying]
[ALEX] It's okay. It's okay.
This time is different.
Worick and Nic aren't like that.
There's the eager lil' beaver.
Man. Seriously, why does
Nicolas hate me so much?
He doesn't.
He just loves giving
the fresh fish a hard time.
Don't you start with me too.
[CODY]
That's all of it.
But I still don't
get why you're--
It's a fairly simple trade.
I'll ID all these
vics for you guys,
and in exchange, Chad lets
us go on our merry way.
How?
Even the boys in the crime
lab are at a total loss.
Their faces were bashed in and
we found no personal belongings.
There's no way you can help us.
Yeah, 'cept the thing is, I can.
[CODY]
Huh?
Number two, the white guy's arm.
Tattoo artist was Edmond.
You're gonna wanna
write this down.
[WORICK] Number seven was one
of Doctor Theo's patients.
Burn marks on his back
are old scars.
Number nine, the redhead,
was a hooker over at Harold's.
Didn't attract much attention.
But I saw her hanging
around numbers 11 and 23
at Connie's shop
not too long ago.
And number 26...
So how's the broad doin'?
[CHAD]
She still with you guys?
If you care about her,
you oughta cut her loose 'fore
she winds up like Veronica.
Here. Done.
That's pretty much everything
I can give you on those stiffs.
[CODY]
Yeah, but, Worick...
How did you--?
Eh, it's nothin'.
Just always been real good
at memorizin' shit.
Let's continue.
In the East-West War
of Unification,
[TEACHER, WALLACE]
the west developed
the bio-enhancement
drug Celebrer
[WALLACE]
and began to issue it.
Soon, the soldiers
who demonstrated
the most improvement
in physical ability
were deployed into combat.
But following reports of
crippling dependency,
many instances of
severe memory loss,
and even death stemming
from its toxicity,
the drug's use was prohibited
upon the war's end.
I've learned it all.
Don't bother coming in tomorrow.
That's not going to happen.
Master Domenico hired me to
give you a proper education
so the Arcangelo
family can maintain
its sterling reputation.
[GASTON] Master Wallace,
this way, please.
[GASTON] For the next six
months, starting today,
we'll be providing security
for the mansion.
[GASTON, WALLACE] I'm head
of the Westgate Mercenaries
[WALLACE]
Captain Gaston Brown.
Up until last week,
you were in charge of quashing
the anti-Twilight faction.
Honor to meet ya.
[WALLACE]
So... who's that?
[phone ringing]
Yeah, hello.
[gunfire]
What's that damn racket?
You start another
freakin' war, Danny?!
[NICOLAS]
Again?
That guy's really gotta start
thinkin' about his age.
[MONROE]
I called the Handymen,
but that new girl of theirs
told me they were at
the station with you.
Could use some backup. Tell
those boys to get down here.
Quicker the better, Chad.
[CHAD] Jesus, sounds like
a pretty rough battle.
You sure you don't want
us to join in, too?
[MONROE]
That's a generous offer, but...
...the Handymen would be...
...a little more expendable
in case anything should go awry.
[CHAD]
Damn, you are one cold bastard!
I thought these boys
were like sons to you!
Just send 'em
the hell down here.
Hey, wait a--
Shit.
[CHAD]
What's the use?
Go on!
Here.
But, Chad, they--!
Doesn't matter now. Forget 'em.
And bring me those damn files.
He's got another
new bodyguard again?
That kid is a real handful.
Not at all like the
missus, now, is he?
[MAID B]
Oh, you don't know?
The master keeps a cheap
prostitute on the side.
[TEACHER A]
The children of Celebrer-users
exhibit pronounced
genomic mutations.
For example,
their physical abilities
become unusually developed,
albeit at the expense of their
mental and emotional faculties.
In turn, many of these cases
require daily use of the drug.
While individuals vary,
on average,
these "Celebrer babies"
suffer shorter lifespans.
A trait that's earned them the
name "Tasogare," or "Twilights."
So, hey. You got a name?
Dude, you deaf?
Answer me!
Um, how come you
won't talk to me?
As your master, I order you to!
Now answer the question!
Unless my father-- Did my
dad order you not to talk?
Is that it?
[NICOLAS]
Eh.
Gone.
I can't hear.
Huh?
[WORICK]
Partners, Nic!
The kind who
stick together! C'mon!
You're too fast. Take pity
on a poor smoker, will ya?
You know damn well
I'm not going home.
[WORICK]
Call it loyalty,
call it a sense of
concern, whatever.
Trouble is, Mister Monroe's
a bit of a loose cannon.
Meaning we need to settle this
now, before it really blows up.
Well, if it isn't the Handymen.
Where are you boys
off to in such a rush?
Business, Granny!
Ah, criminy.
Those two are always gettin'
their asses into somethin'.
[clapping]
[IVAN chuckles]
Ah, nicely done.
But all this ruthless
efficiency, Delico,
makes things kinda dull.
Please... don't kill me.
[gunshot]
This is work, Ivan.
I take pride in it.
[chuckles]
[DELICO]
Let's get back to the boss.
What about the mess?
[DELICO]
That is a lot of bodies.
We could reach out
to Inspector Adkins.
Lemme call him, see what he--
[GANG MEMBER B]
What the hell?
[GANG MEMBER A]
Hey. Kid, you okay?
Shit, get back. He's with them!
Kid's a Twilight!
[ALL gasp]
Damn!
Heh. You're good.
But that don't mean you
can play in my league.
[DELICO]
He's no child.
[DOUG]
Hey, Danny Monroe!
I thought you'd have better
bodyguards than these jokers!
[DELICO]
Not good.
Go link up with the
other unit. I'll handle him.
[GANG MEMBER D]
Hey.
They're all friggin' monsters.
[YANG]
The attack's stopped.
Think we may've been too quick
to call the Handymen
for back up.
--[phone buzzing]
--Hold on.
Hey, kid.
[GANG MEMBER G] You shouldn't
be out here, sport...
Delico, what's up?
[DELICO]
Yang! One got away from us!
Young male, looks like a kid.
Watch out for the little punk!
Don't let him get near the boss!
He's a Twilight!
[gasps]
[MONROE]
Hmm.
S'one agile little fucker.
Ya screwed up, Yang.
I'm sorry, sir.
[MONROE] I'm worried this
twerp's gonna spoil dinner.
I wanna show up with
you guys not dead.
You can take him, right?
[YANG, DIEGO, MILES]
Yes, sir!
[NICOLAS sniffs]
What? Why'd you stop?
Dammit, Nic!
Ugh. That's ripe.
Hey, he was one of Monroe's men.
What're you thinking about
these super clean cuts?
Looks like something
your blade--
Ah, hell. Is it?
So, uh. Hey, Chad.
Can we talk about
what Worick did?
This smells fishy.
[CODY]
Huh?
Reminds me of all the crap
that led up to the Twilight
hunts 15 years ago.
[DOUG]
Aw, dammit!
I just stole this hoodie, too!
Now I know why they call him
"Gunslinger Danny."
Sure he's an old man, but his
aim's still fresh as ever.
--[MILES] That voice.
--[DIEGO] It's him.
I'm so flattered by
your kind words.
[chuckles]
Y'know, I find it hard to
believe that in this city
where the Three Laws've
been in effect for 20 years,
we still have to put up with
dumb little shits like you.
Oh, excuse me.
I mean with rebellious,
acrobatic daredevils like you.
You're startin' to
piss me off, dude.
If I hadn't promised to
bring you back whole,
I'd chop off that
ugly head of yours
and shove it right up
your wrinkly old ass.
Terrifyin', truly.
[DOUG] Well don't try cryin'
to me later, you fuckin' Normal!
[PUNK D]
Awesome. He's decimatin' 'em.
Man, we shoulda just hired
a Twilight from the jump
and been done with it.
[PUNK C] But are ya sure it's
cool we went to a guy like him
without askin' first?
If the boss finds out--
[PUNK D] He won't if
we keep our mouths shut.
And once Monroe's in the bag,
the Cristiano family
will be a breeze.
Hey, sweet-cheeks.
--[thudding]
--[PUNKS groaning]
You don't mind if I ask you
a couple questions, now do you?
[MAID A]
Young Master?
Young Master Wallace?
Sheesh, that boy is too much.
I swear, he must be defective.
[WALLACE] I'm defective?
He's the one who's defective.
If he can't hear, how's he
supposed to protect me?
Makes no sense.
I mean, Michel and Mom,
they have real... real--
[WALLACE]
Don't come in here! Get out!
Um, I, uh...
Sorry--
[NICOLAS] I can't read this,
so I'm returning it.
I, uh, guess I never
got your name.
I'm Wallace. Wallace Arcangelo.
And you?
[WORICK]
Nic, hold on.
Nicolas!
That pile of bodies
they found in District Six
could be his handiwork, too.
If so, he's an
unpredictable head case
with no regard for
the Three Laws.
You get that, right?
So don't do anything stupid,
you reckless bastard.
[MONROE]
Things are gettin' outta hand.
No! Boss!
[DOUG]
Gotcha!
[DOUG] Quick moves.
But I nicked you, too.
[DOUG]
Ah, so that's it.
I knew there was somethin'
off about you earlier.
You wear the tags, but
you don't show 'em off.
Plus, you're weak.
For real, the great Monroe
family hires only one Twilight,
and it's a chickenshit like you?
[MONROE] Hey, even a Low like
this one can serve a purpose.
For instance,
he makes a good shield.
Hmm... But I don't
remember sayin' that.
[gasps]
About us havin' only one
Twilight on our payroll.
Nico!
[MILES]
Handyman!
[DOUG]
Son of a bitch.
You boys have seen some
shit workin' for me,
but you've never seen two guys
ranked this high go at it.
This oughta be fun.
[BOTH]
Boss, should we--?
[MONROE] All right, gents.
Time to place your bets.
[MONROE]
Who's your money on?