Look at that one, honey!
The long, flowing tentacles...
It's like the
snow-white lace on
the dress of a
princess, isn't it?
Tell ya what, Tsukimi. When
you grow up and get married,
I'll make you a dress
just like these jellyfish.
When I was little... There
was a jellyfish aquarium that
my mom used to
take me to visit.
I'm sorry, does
that sound weird?
When she saw the fluttering
frills on the jellyfish that
looked like a princess's
dress, Mom told me...
That's not weird, Mom. I would
love a jellyfish wedding dress!
They're so... pretty!
"When they grow up...
All little girls can
blossom into
beautiful princesses."
What? Dreaded Shibuya?!
Have you gone mad?
Shibuya, on a weekend?!
And you would
risk going there alone?
Oh, the horror! One time,
when I went there...
But still you insist on taking
this perilous journey, hah?!
Then live, Tsukimi! Please!
Come back to us alive!
Hi, Mom. Well, you were right.
It's been six months
already since I moved to
Tokyo to try and make
it as an illustrator.
Here, in this sprawling
spectacle of a metropolis,
there are lots of princesses.
But... I'm sorry, Mom. That's
where the bad news comes in.
I'm not sure where I went wrong,
but somewhere along the way,
instead of becoming
a beautiful princess...
Ho-Home... I'll just go home.
Somehow, I just
ended up being a freak.
Tsukimi has returned to us!
Tsukimi Kurashita,
age eighteen!
I have returned from
Shibuya alive and well!
Lady Tsukimi! Thank
goodness you're home safe!
Yeah so... Before I
could even make it to
the photo exhibit
at that "Parco" place,
I was hit with dizziness,
heart palpitations,
and shortness of breath, forcing
humbling and tearful retreat.
That happened to me too...
Ohhh! So even your great love
of jellyfish could not guide you
through that
maelstrom of madness!
You were right. I should
have just gone on a weekday.
The crowd at the
station was especially huge.
I had the same problem when I--
It's always been a
traffic hub. In the Sixties,
the old Tamagawa
streetcars were packed.
Cool.
They carried me to
the station office one time
when I was
swooning from anemia.
Don't know whether
it's even worth
giving it another
shot tomorrow.
You reckless
lover of adventure!
I wouldn't do it,
Tsukimi. In fact, you were
lucky to make it
back alive this time.
So Mom... Even though I
didn't manage to blossom into
a beautiful princess...
I do have a really
fun life here in Tokyo.
It wasn't a total loss though.
I did manage to get the
things you all requested.
Oh! Joy!
Let's see... This is what you
were askin' about, right Banba?
Mmm... yeah.
I made some new friends online,
and about three months ago,
they invited me to move into
their communal
apartment building.
I've been living
here ever since.
All the residents are so nice.
Very considerate of each other.
And I'm happy to report
they're all a lot like me!
Okay, here you go, Mayaya,
straight from
Aki-habara Station.
Three Kingdoms
Mini-Figures, Akihabara-style!
I didn't open any of 'em.
Yep, they're all freaks.
Shee-AH-ho DOON!
Shee-AH-ho Yu-WAN! Tsao Tsao!
Welcome to the Nunnery,
honored warriors!
Kingdom of Wei in the house!
We've all got our
own different interests.
But like me, they're
all otaku to the core.
I'm so sorry! It got
all crumpled in the crowd.
And of course...
None of us have boyfriends.
Wish I could
see his rumply hair!
So we came up with a slightly
tongue-in-cheek nickname for us.
We call ourselves...
The Sisterhood.
Another email from
someone who wants to
live here at Ama-mizu-kan.
I wish they'd stop.
Yes, there's a vacancy,
but "if we don't know ya,
someone's gotta vouch for ya."
There've been a
lot of these, huh?
I guess the
Sisterhood community is
bigger than I realized.
And it's such a hassle to have
to turn down every single one.
Maybe we should settle on some
rules to post for applicants.
Times like this
call for one thing.
We must consult Ms. Mejiro!
Good plan! Why
don't you take care of
writing the note
this time, Mayaya?
I accept! Whoosh!
"More and more people
are asking to live here.
We'd like to post clear and
simple application requirements
on the community
home page, but..."
Sure. This'll work nicely.
Most honored Ms. Mejiro!
We humbly request your wisdom!
Did I... see a bike
courier here this morning?
Yes... She just
made her deadline,
so she's most
likely relaxing today.
So, do you think she
might come out of her room?
She's anthropophobic
and nocturnal...
And as a best-selling
manga artist who
was called "the Grand
Dame of Boys' Love,"
her extremely rare days
off are devoted to sleeping.
Yeah, I know, it's just I'd like
to at least see her sometime.
Iriomote wildcats.
What?!
Sightings of both are
just as rare. Mother made me
acting building
superintendent five years ago,
and even I've only seen her
barely a handful
of times since then.
Here it comes!
That's our Ms. Mejiro!
The last time my mom was
able to take me someplace...
it was to that same quiet little
jellyfish aquarium by the sea...
in our hometown of Kagoshima.
The snow-white jellyfish
we gazed at together were the
most beautiful things
my young eyes had ever seen,
and I was completely
enchanted by them.
Look, Mom! This one's
a Flower Hat Jelly!
See all the pretty colors?
This is a Spotted Jelly!
The book says that's cuz it
looks like a Spotted Octopus!
Wow! You've become
quite the expert, Tsukimi...
Yup! Oh! And check this out!
When you write out the
kanji for "jellyfish," it's
spelled "sea" and "moon."
But if you flip that to "moon"
and "sea," it spells "Tsukimi!"
Fess up, Mom! Did you
name me after a jellyfish?
Even I'm not silly enough
to name you after a jellyfish!
You know this story! I named
you "Tsukimi" because you were
born by the sea on a
night when the moon was
at its most beautiful.
Oh yeah, forgot!
So on those really lonely
days... those days when
I miss her the most...
I always go visit Clara.
Hi, Clara! How've you been?
Guess it's been a couple days!
Dang, you've got it good.
Wish I could float
around with you.
Oh... Hey, you've
got a new frie--
Is that... Is
that a Moon Jelly?
No! This is bad! I read
if you put a Spotted Jelly
and a Moon Jelly in
the same tank together,
the Spotted one
will weaken and die!
The shopkeeper must
not know! I have to te--
It's...!
It's... one of the
Stylish! And it's a boy!
We're doomed! I couldn't
talk to a Stylish boy even if
we were the last two
people on Earth! But...
Tsukimi! Please help me!
Clara?
Please Tsukimi!
You have to help me!
Clara!
Please hurry! I'm
freakin' dyin' over here!
Cuh-lara!
Tsukimi!
Claraaaaa!
Tsu-ki-mi!
Clara!
She stood up! She stood up!
Clara stood up! Clara stood up!
Yeah, what? Can't you see we're
like, closed... and stuff?
Over uh...
Over--tank--over--there...
Yeah?
In-in-the-Sp-Spotted
Jelly, w-w-with the tank,
a-and the M-Moon Jelly--?
Huh?
I'm certain you are aware
of the incredible intricacies
and difficulties involved
in raising jellyfish.
It is generally accepted among
breeders that if a Spotted Jelly
and a Moon Jelly are raised
together in such a small tank,
the Spotted Jelly, a member
of the order Rhizostomee-eye,
will become weakened
by the mucus secreted by
the Moon Jelly and die.
Honestly, why you would even...
Yeah, so... listen...
Boss'll be in tomorrow.
Thank you, come again!
Tomo--rrow--too--late!
Whoa! What the crap?!
Do I gotta call the cops?!
Leggo!
You hafta--
Back off! Dammitall...
I'm serious! Get! Out!
Crazy freakin' otaku!
Ooh... you okay, hon?
Excuse me! I just...
I couldn't believe it, Mom...
The person standing right there
in front of me...
She was a princess!
Commercial Message!
Clara!
Aaand we're back!
Tequila.
Lovers' quarrel?
No! Why would I ever go
out with someone like that?!
I don't even know this chick.
So what then,
you just knocked over
some girl you
"don't even know?"
Yeah well, she was
like, talking all crazy
and tryin' to
come up in here...
No... wait! I
just wanted him...
to transfer that
jellyfish to a different tank!
'Cause if he
doesn't soon, it'll die!
Die you say?
Yes! Die!
Why don't you just take it?
Give us that one. Hop to,
shop boy. What's the problem?
Well y'see, my boss...
You can just tell him
the poor thing died earlier!
If you don't do something,
that's what'll happen anyway.
Right? You said that it would
die soon? This... jelly-thing?
Huh? Uh, yes! It'll die!
It's... It's already
dead, if that helps!
Jellyfish sure need a
lot of stuff! Here I thought
all you had to do was
drop 'em in some water.
Yeah, I'm sorry...
I can pay you back
as soon as I
get home though.
No, forget about
it! This was fun!
That's what you call "fun?"
Which way?
Huh? Oh! Uh... this way!
Next stop is Shibuya. Change
here for the following lines:
Tokyu Toyoko, Den-en-toshi,
Keio Ino-kashira,
Hanzomon and
the Ginza Subway.
Oh! You have such a
lovely figure, Midoriko!
It looks perfect on you!
I shall not waste
my father's essence...
nor my mother's blood!
Curse you, Tsao Shing!
Oh, good! Nobody's up!
Oh! What a fabulous building!
Shh! Could you
please lower your voice!
How come? Do
you have a curfew?
No, but it-- it might
be bad if the other tenants
saw someone
like you in here...
What?!
Wait! No! I didn't mean it
like-- it's just-- you're like
a whole other
species from them.
Like from a
different world, I guess.
Ah, so you can
tell then, can you?
Sorry 'bout this, Clara...
I'll buy you a proper tank first
thing in the morning, 'kay?
Hey! She's swimming!
Oh, thank goodness.
So uh... I can't
thank you enough.
You're totally
like, Clara's savior.
"Savior's" a bit much.
Yeah... So, you see, um...
I'm real sorry to
hafta ask you this...
But... would you
mind going away now?
Go! Through
the window! Quick!
What? Way up there? No way.
Ack! One of the Stylish!
Oh gosh, no! Mayaya's
completely turned to stone!
C'mon! Snap out of it!
Who the heck is this
intruder woman, huh?! Ah!
There's a jellyfish
in the bathtub!
Ah! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Did you draw all these?
Pictures of jellyfish?
What's this one
that looks like beads?
That's a... Flower Hat Jelly.
And this one?
A Comb Jelly.
They sparkle.
Yes, although strictly
speaking, Comb Jellies are
actually ctenophores, not
cnidarians like true jellyfish.
The cilia in those lines
on their bodies reflect light
like glittering rainbows,
they're as beautiful as any--
Oh, this one's gorgeous!
It's like... it
reminds me of lace...
Snow-white lace.
Can I use this a sec?
I was out all night
partying again, I am so wiped.
Just a lil power nap, 'kay?
She's out?!
Woah! Shibuya? Now you would
venture to dreaded Shibuya?!
Yes. My favorite butler,
Tokiwazaka, is working today
only at their location there...
Where Tsukimi
was slain in battle!
Do you go to seek revenge?!
Do you go, even though I,
Guan Yu, warn you not to?!
I think I'll be fine...
just for the occasion--
In Shibuya... Those
power failures from the
Ginza Line's third
rail made everything crazy.
Just for the occasion--
Girls! What on earth
happened to the bathroom?
Just for the occasion...
I bought a whole bunch
of iron pills!
Oh, right... She passed
out here last night...
It's... a wig?
Now that think of it, I
remember reading the Stylish
are all into a wig fad lately.
Now that's a look
that'd turn people to stone!
Wow, Mom... I never
realized such beautiful people
like her existed.
Give us that one... Hop to,
shop boy! What's the problem?
She's tall, and fair-skinned,
with big, bright eyes...
Like some real-life
Barbie doll...
She's bold and brash,
using her beauty as a weapon.
Basically, the
complete opposite of me.
She actually did
grow up to be a princess.
S'a great wig, huh?
I'm so sorry! I don't--!
Found it online... For like,
12 thousand yen? 13 maybe?
Ah jeez... Sorry...
Didn't I tell ya last night?
Tsukimi!
Am-m-m-m-m-m...
Am-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m-m--
What's with all the
shoving? Yeah, I'm a man.
A-Are you a drag queen?
What? No! Cross-dressing's
just my hobby... I'm... normal.
"Normal?!" I'd say
you're anything but!
Anyhoo, bum
some makeup remover?
I fell asleep with this
on. My face is all... bleh!
I don't... I don't
own any such thing!
Wha-- You don't? Why not?
"W-Why not?" Well, you see...
I am not in the particular habit
of painting my
face in order to meet
archaic social standards
that have no bearing on--
You don't wear makeup at all?
No, no, I don't! Oh, but they
did put lipstick on me one time
when I graduated grade school!
What're you lookin' at?!
Waitaminit are
you a... virgin?
Clara here! Coming in
at Number One on this week's
"Top Five Things You Shouldn't
Ask the Sisterhood" is...
"Are you a virgin!"
Vuh... vuh...
Oh, I get it, that's why
you're so bent outta shape.
Don't worry, I'm not
gonna attack you.
Ah, bummer...
I guess soap it is.
Please do not
go out this door!
Why not? The sink's
out there, isn't it?
The point is you can't
go out there like that!
Please-please-please
put on some clothes!
And don't forget
your wig and lady bits!
Tsukimi! Are you awake?
Well Mom, I finally met
a princess here in Tokyo...
She's strong, and she's
beautiful... and she's a boy!