I have this secret
hiding in my closet.
Mama, this house is
amazing. It's super gigantic!
That's right, Kuranosuke.
If you get good grades,
I bet Papa will get
you whatever you want.
Really? Do you think
he'd buy me clothes?
Of course he will.
He's got plenty of money.
Dude, what's up with your lame-o
glasses? One, they're huge.
Two, they're...
nah one was enough.
I must have
lost mine somewhere.
I'm getting a new pair now.
Well, crap.
I can't just...
up and ask him...
"Hey Bro, so you're still a
virgin at 30. Is that 'cause you
got your brain fried seeing
your dad and my mom making out
like a couple horny
teenagers in the wardrobe room
backstage at some
theater or whatever?"
Man... that's too
bold even for me.
What? You're
telling me you haven't
fixed the
Amamizu-kan deal yet?
Why the hell is Acquisitions
taking so long on this?
That place is a beast. We
need to tear it down first.
Uh, well, they did get a
verbal agreement from them.
It's just... the owner's
been traveling overseas,
so scheduling a time for closing
has been a little tricky.
They think it could
come together by next month.
What? Why next month? It's
too late. This is me leaving.
I've got work in the
neighborhood anyway.
I have to return a little
something to my boyfriend.
Nice to see you
all again. Remember me
from Global City Create?
That "woosh" noise.
Uh, was that them?
Hi! Clara's here to help! The
Banba Scope can analyze any bag.
And based on its logo,
size and relative weight,
can determine its
most likely contents.
Doesn't even matter what's
inside! It could be meat,
desserts, squid, sea
urchin, or any number of
high-purine seafood.
Banba has an uncanny
and intuitive
knowledge of that as well.
It really is quite remarkable.
'Kay listen up, that vixen's
totally got snacks in the bag.
Really? Ah, I bet it's
only plain rice crackers.
I don't think so... Judging from
the logo design and bag size,
I'm thinking it's
from a bakery. A good one.
I'm bettin' macarons.
Muh! macarons?
Hello, I am the
manager of this building.
Please tell me what
I can do for you today?
You have to be the owner's
daughter! I'm sorry to show up
unannounced like this...
I was in the neighborhood so
I thought I'd
come say "hello."
The vixen attacks!
Mayaya! Why on earth are you
coming in through the window?
You do realize I'm on
the second floor, don't you?
But... the Vixen!
The Vixen's here?
Oh yeah, she's here!
Invading our sacred land!
She's come from the
depths of Hell, oh yeah!
Come to take our
souls, good lord!
And to buy our home, oh no!
Depths of Hell I
say, depths of Hell!
Yay! We got macarons!
Macarons?!
Why was she here?
They're from that
place Yakkun was
raving about
on Hanamaru Market.
What the heck? She
left some glasses in here.
I wonder whose they are...
Sorry. Silly me. It seems I
accidentally left something
in that bag I dropped off.
Oh my... What a curious
room... So... unique.
Stay out!
Oh great. You found them... I'll
just get out of your way then.
One more thing...
Minister Koibuchi's
residence is nearby, isn't it?
Yeah, it's about...
10 or 15 minutes on foot.
You some kind of spy?
Not at all, I'm just going
to return something that
got left behind. Now,
if you'll excuse me.
Well... please be sure to
drop me a line, as soon as
your mother comes home.
It won't take long to
explain the contract to her.
Okay! I'm really
going this time.
Who're you?
Do you live here young lady?
You bet your butt I do.
No he doesn't!
Well in that case,
here's my card. Feel free to
contact me if you have any--
I shoulda known! What's wrong?
Why aren't you all
dressed in your battle gear?
Because... they didn't
warn us... before they came.
Figures...
Hey! You landsharks.
I'm gonna talk real
loud so you'll understand.
Nobody here has any
intention of leaving.
So you might as well go
tell your bosses you can't get
Amamizu-kan to sell, 'cause
it's just too Tom Cruise!
Mission Impossible!
Huh? Izzat so? I thought the
building owner got to decide.
Owner... Yeah, I guess
you're right. Then we'll just
make sure this place gets
bought before you tear it down.
Sorry... I don't
follow your logic.
Maybe we'll decide to buy it.
Right, that's funny!
Good luck with that.
Do you have any idea
how much this place costs?
I don't care. A hundred
million? A billion?
Nothing's going to stop us.
No matter how much it costs...
We'll buy it.
Mayaya, throw some salt.
On it!
Woo! Salt assault!
Be gone you evil spirits.
It's working!
Keep throwing. Go home!
Next time bring your
cute older boss man with you.
No... Wait!
Atta girls! Defend that door!
Problem solved!
That wasn't so hard!
Yeah, um... How's it solved?
Ah no worries, seriously!
My family is totally super rich.
Plus I've got
some dirt on my dad.
Please stop
saying things you have
no intention of
following through on.
What do you mean? Chieko
is just going to walk right up
to her mother when
she gets back and say,
"Yo Mom, I wanna
buy your building."
What? Ridiculous. She'd
kill me just for saying "yo."
Hey, um...? Can we...
go talk somewhere?
This is different. It's
not every day you invite me out
to a park. What is
going on with you, Tsukimi?
Nothing. I just
wanted... to talk.
So, that woman who just
came by... is she? Your buh--?
Boogieman?
No... is she your big brother's,
I dunno... girlfriend?
N-Not that I care either way...
Wait a minute. You think
my brother has a girlfriend?
Yes... I'm sure... She was
returning his glasses to him...
like he'd left them
at her house or something.
Glasses, huh? Wait
when he came home yesterday
he wasn't wearing them...
And this morning when
I saw him he had on his
old institutionally
huge 90's pair.
Please, do not tell
me... they're "doing it?!"
Hey... are you okay?
I walked right past
them. The two of them...
they were
definitely together.
Tsukimi... What are
you crying for? Why--?
You smell nice... Is that
a new perfume you're wearing?
So um... Technically I
am still a guy, you know.
Oh yeah...
I guess you are, huh?
Ahah! Lesbians!
Buzz off, y'snotheads.
I'm gonna go wash my face.
Commercial Message!
Clara.
Now the other part.
Tequila.
Really? Three figure balances!
No! Mine has only
two figures this month!
Why are you so broke?
I shouldn't have yelled. Not
like I expected you guys to have
much in the way
of savings anyway...
Money, money,
money, whatever...
What's your damage,
Scrooge McChick?
It's like I keep telling you,
we've got to buy this place.
Hey! What's so funny?
Oh, just let it go. That
joke was never funny anyway...
A true Katsura Comedy
master would know that.
This is not a joke! I'm
dead serious.
If we put our minds
to it, we can make
all the money we need.
Look at all the talent here.
Am I right, Mom? He's
completely nuts, isn't he?
I have no idea where
he comes up with this stuff.
Oh! Maybe he's an alien...
But then, rich people
all seem like aliens to me...
Still somehow we
all keep getting swept up
in his wacky hijinks. When
he's around, it's hard not to
feel excited about
what the day may bring.
So... I would just like to
say that girl was smokin' hot.
You listen here!
She was just fooling you
with her makeup, moron!
If you scrubbed her face
clean, you'd see there was
nothing underneath there
at all! Her lashes were those
fake Hollywood Legends
ones everyone thinks
are hot right now.
Betty Davis?
There's other
styles, but who cares?
It's how you wear them that
counts! Now agree with me
before I find another
way to make you suffer!
Yes... Right as always but
she still had a
body that wouldn't quit.
Gag me, ugh! It figures
you'd like a skinny broomstick
like her you friggin' idjit.
Do you not realize nobody that
skinny has boobs like those?!
Fat deposits do not work that
way. They do not, not, not, not!
Sorry I'm not some twig
with a ridiculous boob job
that makes my breasts defy
gravity and sparkle like candy!
You're making a scene.
Are you crazy. Stop it.
We'll get arrested.
Enough with the whining! I'll
wreck all the rundown buildings
in this neighborhood,
and then, I'll drop a giant,
soul crushing
hotel on their ruins!
Perhaps we should
use our inside voice.
Creepy... What is this room?
Some bizarre "Doll Graveyard?"
How dare you say that?!
I graciously open up a
precious corner of my life
to you and you poop in it!
These give me the willies. Which
one's hair grows 'cause it's
possessed by a little girl?
This one's the
worst. Let's sell it.
Sakurako!
Now, say that
again, I dare you!
Whoa... Torpedo...
I double dare you!
No... Listen! I'm saying
you should sell these to
put towards our
Amamizu-kan Purchase Fund.
You wanna just sell 'em
off them as if they're some
cheap trinkets that
have no meaning to me?
They're only dolls, Chieko!
No, they're alive! Each
and every one is my living,
breathing child,
don't you see?
Sakurako, Midoriko...
Tell me, what did
Sakurako set you back?
200 grand.
O Chiyo! Matsuko! O Take!
Bondo! Umeko! Kawako! Reiko!
Do not become that person.
Maybe you don't get it,
but to Chieko... these dolls
might as well be her
family. She can't lose them.
Like that guy who
married his anime pillow!
Shut up.
I suggest you get out
of this room right now.
Okay here's your-- Whoa!
Naked man! Naked man!
Would you just get
used to it already?
Please put some clothes on!
Ah, I would but my
shoulders are all stiff.
What's with you? If my memory
serves, you had no problem
hanging all
over me in the park.
I did not! Not all over.
Got a tea leaf on ya.
A decree! You! Miss Stylish,
girl! Please tell me that you
have a fax machine
at your mansion and
then tell me you'll
let us use it right now.
Okay, home sweet home.
I'm sorry for
making you drive me.
It was such a silly little
errand. You're a patient man.
It's... kinda my job.
Though,  I'm not sure
you needed to rush
out for new ones.
Look.
I had business in
the neighborhood anyway.
I'm glad I was able to bump
into you. Though it seems
I'm a little late by the looks
of those cute new specs I see.
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
Heave-ho. Heave-ho...
But you look so very
serious. What's troubling you?
Trust me... It'll be just
between us. I won't tell a soul.
Actually, I would
like to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
That night... Did we have...
um, s-suh... suh...
Sexual relations?
I apologize, my memory is
hazy, I was quite inebriated.
But I don't recall
anything actually happening.
And more to the point... I
don't believe I'm the kind of
person who could
do that, so you see...
Here. All the proof
you need that we made love.
Oh god... Oh god... I almost
just mouth-faced a girl who's
practically a character straight
out of a Shigeru Mizuki manga!
What the heck's
come over me?!
How do you do it?
How can you just sit there
calmly drinking tea
like nothing happened?
You're messed up!
What are you talking about?
So now you're saying you
don't even know what I did
'cause you had your
eyes closed? I'm an idiot!
No, you can't hold
the manuscript like that,
or you'll crease it.
Those're worth 20,000 yen
per page, for
cryin' out loud!
You have to be
careful with it.
Really? This stuff
makes that much?
So... times how
many hundred pages?
We humbly request your decree.
You'd think we
could text or email her.
Who writes notes on
paper anymore? Not this boy.
Sh... If she finds out
you're male you'll be killed
in a slow and cruel manner.
Sweet! We've got our
down payment. So, now...
My hearing must be going...
What did you say?
You heard me. I'm going
to buy an apartment building
and I need a loan.
Yeah? How much?
I don't know exactly...
Guess about 300 million?
I've got an early morning.
I think I'll turn in.
Hanamori told me you know...
the reason why Shu
can't handle women.
And you think that you
can blackmail me with that?
Yeah... Whenever you
went to see Mom's shows
you guys would totally
do it right in front of Shu.
I can see why he'd
be so traumatized.
Kuranosuke, I only
have one thing to say.
The one time that did happen...
I barely made it to second base.
Watchin' your pops
get to second base with
someone who's not your mom...
That'd mess with a kid's head...
But as blackmail
it's a little weak.
I know...
Hey... Still no touching.
What's up with this look?
Awful conservative for you.
Got an exam today.
Figure cross-dressing
might be a bad idea.
Good call.
Hey dude, this Benz
you're always making sweet,
sweet love to with a
shammy... how much is it worth?
Mercedes Benz S-Class. Base
price: Fifteen million yen.
Whoa, that's
more than I thought.
How many Benzes
do we have again?
Only three.
Only?
Look, it's Kuranosuke!
How come you never
hang out with us anymore?
Yeah sorry, ladies. I've
just been really busy lately.
What about today? Aren't you
free? Let's go out someplace.
Yeah, c'mon!
What is today?
Yeah, we miss you!
What? A flea market?
No arguing. I've
already reserved us a stall.
It's in Harajuku.
Spring cleaning time!
I'm going to completely
clean out your storage.
Stop! You can't!
Mother will be angry!
Whoa there! Why don'tcha
sell off the seemingly
endless supply of fancy
clothes you're always wearing?!
Over my dead body.