Yikes... dust-bunny central!
Get it off!
Now all we gotta do is
track down the good stuff.
Maybe?!
No dice.
Wow... those are great!
Whaddya mean "great?"
These are tacky as hell!
Don't be a snob. Aw, I think
the pattern's really cute!
Fine! Next box!
Her family must be old.
The further back you look,
the dustier the
boxes seem to be...
"Dustier..." Yes, of course!
Change o' plan! Forget the
crap in the front of the room!
It's the golden oldies we want!
The mother lode!
Retro '70s kitchenware!
So lame!
Morons!
Dolphin dishes for the win!
That's my favorite set, also!
Morons... all of ya!
Trendy antique shops are selling
this stuff and making bank!
We could get a hundred
thousand yen, easy.
A hundred thousand?!
Shu. I hear that
developer will be at
next week's
exploratory meeting.
I trust all our materials
are suitably ready?
I'm sorry, Father. Not yet.
Son, go on inside.
I'll be along.
But... yes sir.
Does Shu seem a
little bit... off to you?
He seems like the
same ol' Shu to me.
You know those pricey wheels
you wanted for the Benz?
His glasses... were
returned by a seductress.
So he has a girlfriend?
Looks like he dealt with
his issue and finally had se--
Hey! You idiot, we're out
in public! Not another word!
This leaves us with an
altogether different problem
to solve. Have this
mystery woman looked into.
I'm sorry, sir.
I know I'm in your
personal employ...
But Shu has been my
friend since we were kids.
That's why... I can't bear
to spy on him or his lover.
I refuse.
Fire me if you must.
I'll buy you a
brand new Benz...
Yo. Sugi m'man... Yeah, I need
a background check on somebody.
What? Usual spot? All righty,
see you at the Mr. Doughnut.
That's Sugimoto, an
old school friend of mine
from abacus class. Works
as a private eye these days.
Right. From abacus class.
Okay. I give up. What's this
white thing supposed to be?
Its a little Clara
good luck charm I made.
Hand-made? Wow, that's cool.
This, I'm thinking we could
part with for a hundred yen.
Check it out!
How much do you want?
For you? Three thousand yen!
Huh? Three thousand?!
That's pretty steep!
What? That's a killer price!
These are genuine
Wedgewood mugs we're--
No... not the
mugs, silly! That guy!
Wha--?! This thing?
Yeah, of course!
It is so cute!
Well... how about 500?
Sold!
You always find the good stuff!
She bought it!
It sold!
Tsukimi! Call the girls!
Huh?
What? Any clothing
we don't want?
And a sewing kit?
Bring 'em now? Okay...
She just said if we bring
a sewing kit over to them,
she'll give us 5,000 yen.
Let's hit the road!
One old-fashioned
and... iced coffee.
Hold up. Make that two
of each, why don't ya.
'Sup!
Hey you made it.
Geez... Must be rough,
huh? Growing up political.
Imagine a grown man
having to get every piece of
strange he meets
vetted by his parents?
So... this vamp got a name?
No name, huh?
No worries, friend-o.
Just sketch her for me.
Now draw me a Benz. S-Class.
A Benz S-Class?
Damn, you got chops when
it comes to drawing cars.
Y'ever see a Benz do a hit
and run, their ass is caught.
Uh... those are all I can draw.
Anyway, I'm on the hunt. I'll
see what sorts o' shenanigans
the young master's up to. Oh.
Give my doughnut
a good home, yeah?
Huh? Thank you! I will.
Hey! I'm so glad you came!
We're doomed! This
is Stylish country!
Get back here!
It burns! The fashion. It burns!
Oh, you're fine! I'll gussy
you up again. How's that sound.
Shirt! Wrap! Hat!
And Chieko, you rock it OG.
Again?!
You're not even trying today.
There's too much to do.
That's all I can manage!
Tsukimi! You ready?
Uh, almost... Just a sec...
Huh? Tsukimi?
Say, where has
she scampered away to?
She's right here! Follow the
finger. I dressed her up a bit.
Sorry... I didn't
even know it was you.
Can you find it in your
heart to forgive me, Tsukimi?!
I thought you were
one of those dirty Stylsh,
so I yelled the word
"Die!" in my mind at least
two hundred
times just now.
It's fine. Here. I'll
put my glasses back on.
Please don't die!
Here's the plan. We're all gonna
sit here and make Claras.
Hang on.
Y'mean here, in public?
What's your game?!
We already sold one of 'em.
Whoa. How much'd you
get for it? Like, ten?
Five hundred.
You know, I
don't think jellyfish
come in bright floral print.
Wha? But, you said... I was
supposed to make more Claras
out of these
clothes in the box...
Honestly, Tsukimi! You don't
just grab something willy-nilly!
Finding the perfect fabric
is what fashion is all about!
Check this little beauty out!
Fluttering frills.
Hey you! Going up?
Go on ahead, Father.
I need to use the restroom
before the meeting.
You're doing this
to me why, exactly?
Meet me for drinks tonight
at my building's bar, lover,
and we'll talk all about it.
And if I say no?
Blackmail. Ah. You do
know that's a crime.
Come on. Life is
so boring if you don't
break a few
rules now and then.
The redevelopment
project. Of course.
You want my father
to sign off on it.
Now, don't keep me waiting.
Like a boss!
Look at her go!
Warp Factor Nine!
How can you sew
by hand that fast?!
How can I not? It's a
must for traditional clothing.
I have to start with nothing
more than a bolt of fabric.
"Go big or go
home," as they say.
And, here you are!
It's... It's...
It's... perfect!
Damn!
A Sanderia malayensis!
Her name is Sissy!
Just look at the lovely
lace. It's more than perfect!
She's a brand new character,
and I bet she wants
a little sister, whaddya say?!
You think anyone's gonna
buy a fabric jellyfish?
Not even
Stylish are that dumb!
Even kids are gonna
think they're lame!
Lookit how pretty
the weather charm is!
What's it cost?
Five hundred yen.
No, little girl!
Why do you vex me?!
Y'know, these aren't
charms for good weather.
They're jellyfish dolls!
Huh? Those
squishy ocean things?
Well I'll be! I don't
think I've ever seen
little jellyfish dolls before.
Hey, I want one!
Yeah! I do too!
What are these?
They're adorable!
Hand sewn jellyfish!
Oh, how much?!
Only five hundred!
Too cute! What does it do?
Nothing! It's a jellyfish!
We're gonna need a poster!
Nobody can figure
out what they are!
What... should it say?
Something like, "World's best,
and only, jellyfish dolls!
A unique face on
every one! Buy one now!"
That makes no sense
at all! You're fired!
Trains are not relevant!
Neither is Takeo Chii!
Never mind! Tsukimi, can you--
Perfect! Flower
Hat Jelly! Purple Jelly!
Lion's Mane Jelly!
Spotted Jelly!
Meet the family!
Mayaya! Move all the
ceramic stuff outta the way!
We're goin' full jelly!
Hold on... did we...?!
We sold 'em all!
Commercial message!
Clara!
Are ya ready for more?!
Tequila!
Hey, Chieko! D'you have a piggy
bank 'round here somewhere?
Believe so. Let me check...
Will this work?
A wood bear. Not
quite what I asked...
It looks like wood, but
it's made out of ceramic.
See? Money goes in the slot.
He's been stabbed in the
back by a treacherous yen note!
This knick-knack embodies
the defeat of Earth's wildlife
at the hands of
humanity's greed.
Yeah, whatever.
Huh?
Starting now, we're gonna
save all the money we can.
This is our war chest.
War chest?
Yeah, our bankroll! So
we can make thousands of
jellyfish dolls and
sell 'em on the internet!
Whoa-ho! You're
gonna make us slaves
like those poor kids
in "Temple of Doom!"
Spare me! You guys
don't do squat right now.
Do a little work for a change!
Yo, original Clara here!
Number One on this week's
"Top Five Things You Shouldn't
Ask the Sisterhood..."
"Do... work!" They hate that!
Those who don't work
don't eat, if ya ask me!
Hold up... Where'd
Tsukimi run off to?
Hi, Mom...
Tell ya what, Tsukimi. When
you grow up and get married.
I'll make you a dress
just like these jellyfish.
So, yeah... I know that
girls like me don't get
Prince Charming at the
end of the story, but maybe...
I'm sorry, does
that sound weird?
That a jellyfish would
remind me of a princess?
Y'know... just maybe by some
one-in-a-billion chance...
Tsukimi!
Some guy actually
did want to marry me...
...and if... if you were
still alive to see it...
I'm coming in!
I'd hold you to your
promise... and have you
make my wedding dress...
Tsukimi...?
Have you lost your mind?!
The Hell was that...?!
Fine, I get it. I'll leave.
You're welcome! Good night!
Is it... pounding
'cause I...? No! Hell, no!
That nutjob was
about to jump out
a second-floor
window in front of you.
Of course your pulse is
gonna be all screwy. Yeah...
Crazy day! Oh,
whatta scent! Black tea?
It's roasted tea!
Sounds delish! Mind
if I get in on that?
Of course, dear.
Have some yokan, too.
Aw, you're a doll!
Just what I needed!
It's still pounding!
Stupid heart, you cut
that crap out already!
What-the-crap?!
Emergency! Is it the yokan?!
Are you choking on
its squishy goodness?!
Drink some tea! Stat!
My chest. Ah man,
it's killing me...
She can't breathe!
Vicks VapoRub to the rescue!
Uh, I don't think
that's what she needs!
Impossible... this isn't
happening! I've been a hit with
the ladies since, like,
birth! She's my Waterloo?!
The rack is a lie!
Oh snap.
Arise, Tsukimi!
We've been tricked.
Oh, the humanity!
Huh...?
I ran and got Vicks
VapoRub for that wretch out of
the goodness of my heart,
but when I pulled down
her tube-top to apply
its mentholated magic...
They were fake! Your friend's
not really stacked at all!
She's just a poseur
who wears too much makeup
and hasn't come to terms
with her mosquito-bites!
Good boy. I was
afraid you wouldn't come.
As soon as we're
done here, I'm leaving.
Oolong tea, if you please.
Don't you want
something a little stronger?
No.
You come to a
bar and order tea?
You're a bit of a
tease, aren't you, Shu?
I won't have a drink.
So stop. Just say your piece.
There's no piece. Sorry.
Maybe I just wanted
to see you again.
Well, if you're
not going to drink...
How about you take
this girl for a spin?
Pick you up in
Roppongi? Of course. Huh?
I'm not taking you home?
Strange. Maybe Sugi
can enlighten me.
Uh, hey Sugi. You're trailing
Shu currently, aren'tcha?
He wants me to bring
the car down to Roppongi,
but he was being vague.
Thought he might be with that
mystery girl of his. If so, make
sure you get some clear photos.
Mr. Koibuchi won't
stop pestering me
to find out who she is.
He totally saw! A male Stylish
who makes a prettier girl
than I do saw me
being an absolute dork!
Good job, self! Let's wrap
this ugly, awkward body of ours
in some old sheets
and play "Tsukimi's magical
one-in-a-billion
wedding!" Yeah!
That's a great idea!
My head...
Mom... what the heck
is wrong with me tonight?
My heart-rate's funky and I can
hardly breathe. Man, it sucks!
And how come Tsukimi was
all dressed up like that, huh?
Wrapped up in a sheet,
with a cloth on her head.
A little old to
be playing princess.
But hey,
maybe thanks to me,
she's getting
interested in clothes.
If that's the case...
Wanna know
a secret, Kuranosuke?
Your mama has a big dream!
Here it is! Mama wants to pack
this closet to the gills with
beautiful dresses
from all over the world!
If that's the case...
I wonder... How would
Tsukimi's face look...
if I showed her Mom's closet?
Even if I ever met the right
guy and Mom were still alive...
and she made me a dress of
snow-white lace
like that jellyfish,
it wouldn't even look good on
me. I'd have to be all slender
and pale with big
eyes and long lashes...
I'd have to look...
like him, basically.
Aw, come on! Stop
spazzing out on me!
And you dropped this!
I don't want that old
thing. Jus' throw it away!
Hey, it's nothing to
be embarrassed about!
Every girl plays
"one-woman fashion show"
now and then,
right? No worries!
Well, I wasn't having
a fashion show, okay?!
My mom told me
something a long time ago
and I was testing a hypothesis.
It's perfectly rational!
What'd she say?
Back when my mom
was still alive...
she promised to make me
a dress like a jellyfish!
I hadn't thought
about it in a while,
but making all those
dolls this afternoon...
I... I remembered, and...
Tsukimi...
I know it's stupid.
Please don't tell the others!
Tsukimi! Let's make one!
Let's make one! You and me!
We'll mass-produce 'em!
Sell 'em by the truckload!
We'll be filthy rich, thanks
to your jellyfish dress!
Uh, hold on. Wha...
whaddya mean, we're going to
make the dress?
We'll take all the money
we earn and buy this place!