Hey, Mom, it's Kuranosuke.
I've been having a
pretty good time lately.
You'll never guess
what I found nearby.
An ivory tower filled with
maidens! Well, more like
an old co-op building
stuffed with girl-geeks...
Down but not out,
vowing at a press conference
earlier today that he will
give the task of
revitalizing Japan's economy,
quote, "One-hundred--"
Shu... your uncle is on his
way. Where's your brother?
I'll fetch him.
Ready yet, Kuranosuke? Hello?!
Well? How do I look?!
Check it out!
Kuranosuke... You do
know who's coming over
for lunch, do you not?
'Course I know. Do you think
I forgot? It's Uncle Saburota!
And you're meeting
him dressed like that?!
Yeah-- Why wouldn't I?
C'mon, they're gonna love it!
I went extra-busty for 'em!
Shu! Kuranosuke! Get
down here on the double!
'Kaaaaay!
Do you care to tell me...
what's going through
your head right now?
I am really at a loss here!
Soon as you're in college,
every single day it's
dresses and wigs and padding!
Oh yeah! Let's
get ready to uncle!
Damn it.. He's already inside!
Where does he even
pick up this stuff?
Take that off!
Nah... I'm good! 'Sides, my
dressing up like this helped me
make a bunch of new friends.
The thing I believe in most
is the underlying strength
of my countrymen!
Seems they're running
these ads more and more.
Is there an election coming up?
How am I supposed to
believe in a prime minister
who's got that much
empty scalp? Forget us!
The thing you should
believe in most is a toupee!
He's got family
nearby doesn't he?
I already told you,
it's the Koibuchis!
Prime Minister Negishi
is Koibuchi's wife's brother.
They've been all over the TV.
Family's been
full of politicians
since back before
the war, even.
Tsukimi, what's the matter?!
Why is ectoplasm floating out
of your mouth like that?!
Thanks for coming,
I know you're busy.
Hey, Uncle! I saw
your commercial!
Brother dear wants to know
why I'm in Gaga mode lately?
Two reasons, basically.
Reason the first,
being a politician
would totally suck!
Nobody'll make me be one if they
all think I'm some sort of nut!
Mr. Excitement here can
follow in their footsteps,
leaving me to do
whatever I please!
Kura-poo! Oh! You are
just the cutest thing ever!
Hey... Kuranosuke's
pretty hot, huh.
Uh, yeah... Jus' don't forget
what he's packin' underneath...
My Kura-poo is... so...
Kuranosuke!
Stop that wiggling!
Aw... Dad! Don't
be such a square!
Me an' Unky are jus'
having a good time here!
Dear... stay calm!
If he were any cuter,
I would explode!
Get out of my
sight! No, not you!
That's more like it! Who
wants to waste a beautiful day
having lunch with a couple
of fogeys? Not this boy...
Today's look is especially
fetching, young sir.
Merci beaucoup!
Man, I'm impressed Shu
can even choke down his lunch
with all o' their droning
on about politics...
What's up?
We're still on for tonight
right, Kuranosuke?
Uh, maybe...?
The cosmetics showcase
in Shimokita? Duh!
Oh yeah...
So you're coming, right?
Hmm, nah. I'm out.
Why not? You got
something better planned?
Hanging out with them isn't as
fun as it used to be. I dunno...
All it ever is with them is
music and fashion and sex.
The clouds look
like jellyfish...
Y'know... listening to Tsukimi
geek out about jellyfish has
gotta be a hundred times more
interesting than all that stuff.
Wow! I'da never guessed
you have to take her out
of her tank
just to get her fed.
Speaking of... whaddya
feed her, anyway?
Uh... just cultured
zooplankton from the fish store.
Hey... can I ask you a question?
I mean, like, after this one?
But of course! Today is "French
Lolita meets '20s Flapper!"
No... it's about your fa--
Fangirl?
Uh... no... sorry...
I... heard that, your
family is kind of like,
important in politics...
What's that?
Oh. Hey, Meat.
Ya know... calling people
"Meat..." Not so polite.
Where's the beef? Get it,
Meat? Where's the beef, Meat?
Whoa! Banba! We're
having anmitsu today!
Get outta town! From where?!
This way! This way!
Chieko! Incoming!
That's right, Banba.
It's from Kinozen,
that dessert shop
you're so partial to!
Mayaya bought it for
us on her way home from
a Three Kingdoms
fan fic event!
Thirty-eight
hundred yen?! Pricey!
And there's Bavarian
Cream green tea!
Mind if I ask you
ladies something?
What do... you all
do for a living, anyway?
I mean, I'm just saying...
Plankton and
aquariums are expensive,
and the anmitsu at Kinozen
is like 700 yen a pop!
I thought maybe you
were students or something,
but none of you ever
seem to go to school...
Clara here! Number One on this
week's "Top Five Things You
Shouldn't Ask the Sisterhood!"
Kuranosuke's "What do you
all do for a living, anyway?"
Oh also, "how
old're all of you?"
Well aren't you
a nosy little wench!
As far as your first question
goes, we of the Sisterhood
have a perfectly respectable
income! And it's...
What?
Our allowances!
You... put on... your
game-face to say that?
We're kids of baby boomers. Our
parents lucked out and came of
age during the most prosperous
era in all of Japanese history.
We, on the other hand,
the baby-boomers' babies,
came onto the scene just in
time for the bubble to burst
and leave us idling in the
"Lost Decade." Not enough jobs
to go around and with us
all young and inexperienced,
of course we couldn't
earn enough to pay our bills!
And Mom and Dad were
like, "Mayaya, don't worry.
We'll cover your rent, dear!"
There's no shame in it! What
was I s'posed to do, say no?!
Mayaya... just stop! She
gets it! Everyone gets it!
Wait a sec!
You're boomer kids?!
That means you're
in your thirties, huh!
Asking a woman's
age is very rude!
Well... I'm eight.
Huh?!
Oh yes. Our Banba
was born in a leap year.
Yep. February 29th.
Been eight for a while now.
What you're saying is... This
is headquarters for a bunch of
jobless 30-something
NEET chicks with afros?
That is not what
we are saying at all!
We have jobs,
thank you very much!
I stuff envelopes from
the safety of my room.
Chieko sells homemade
clothes and stuff online.
E-commerce, yo.
Also, we"re assistants
to Ms. Juon Mejiro,
the popular
"Boys Love" manga-ka.
Furthermore, Chieko
has been chosen to
run the building and defend it
from all foes so her mother, our
landlady, can fly to Korea with
little-to-no advance
warning in pursuit
of her favorite actor, Bae!
Wait... that Bae?
Yes, that one!
Fro's legit.
So you see... we
are all... definitely...
not a bunch... of NEETs!
Man, they sure freaked out...
Thought Mayaya was gonna hit me!
Was what I said
really that bad?
Gee, ya think?
Sorry.
Hey, Tsukimi. What were
you going to ask me before?
Oh... that... I saw your brother
and dad, y'know, on TV...
Yeah! I can't change
channels quick enough.
And those neckties? Ugh...
So, um... how
come the son of
a big politician's
dressing... like that?
You wanna know?
Wow. I never saw it before...
Why don't we...
go back to my place?
Let's have some fun...
Huh?
Commercial Message!
Clara!
Are ya ready for more?!
Tequila!
You'll thank me for this!
It's time to free you
from those lifeless rags!
Let's comb that hair!
Tame that unibrow!
Shave those legs!
Reason the second for
dressing the way I do...
The world of
politics is so boring!
For me, it's
fashion or nothing!
Now! Make-up-ocalypse!
Kuranosuke? Are you
holed up in there?
Uncle's on his way home. Put
on some pants and come on ou---
Hey!
Get your ass back he-- uh!
Oops... Did I do that?!
Thanks again for your time.
Hang loose, Bro-in-law!
Another cutie-pie?! What're
you putting in the water?!
No! What'd he do to me?!
I can't look like this!
Get it off, get it off!
If the Sisterhood sees me all
dolled up and
looking like a Stylish,
they'll tie me up in the middle
of Ikebukuro and pelt me with
junk for being a
traitor to geekdom!
'Sup?
Kuranosuke! My makeup and outfit
don't work together at all!
Can you get over here ASAP?
Nah... I think I'll pass.
Say what?!
You guys just aren't enough
of a challenge for me anymore.
Huh?
I've realized something!
Polishing a diamond
in the rough
is tons more fun!
What? My jewelry
isn't the issue here!
Looks like it's go-time, Mom.
I'm gonna put my skills
to the test! Deep down,
all women want to be pretty...
even those freaky spinsters
over at Chez Otaku.
Every girl is born a princess.
Some of 'em just forget is all.
Well, Mom... I was wrong
about that boy I met...
He's no princess.
He's a wicked witch!
Why would he
pick on me like this?
I never did a thing to him!
"Hey, let's slap a dress on
the awkward girl!"
What a laugh, right?
Oh good. Coast is clear.
Among men, Lu Bu!
Among horses, Red Hare!
And among honored women!
Poor departed Banba! Huh?
Chieko, come quick!
Zombie twelve o'clock!
It wants to knock us
down and eat our brains!
Clara!
What's all the fuss about? Good
lord, girl, that face of yours!
You look like a
Chinese hopping vampire!
She totally does.
Oh, so that's jus' cosplay!
Why didn't you say so?!
Gonna getcha!
She's on the prowl!
My jugular is off-limits!
It's my blood
an' I'm keeping it!
That's right,
you hop up there!
Hey! Bring me some garlic!
I am gonna clove
the crap outta you!
Uh, Mayaya... you're
on Banba's hair. Yoo-hoo?
That was close!
Please tell me I still
have that old pair of
glasses with
the cracked lens.
Please please please!
Yay for high-school glasses...
Whoa. Vampire's right!
What a spaz that
girl is. Ran outta here
without her
glasses and sweats...
Kuranosuke... I...
wanted to ask you about...
Uh... well... what're your
thoughts on... the new...
i-increase in the sales tax?
It's bad?
Ah.
Hi again...
Yeah hi...! What?!
That friend of yours,
the girl who just ran off...
D'you... know her
from school or somesuch?
Ooh! You like her?!
So you noticed a chick?!
Our little Shu's all growsed up!
What?! No! I'm just
making conversation!
I could introduce ya!
For the low, low price
of my mom's address.
You know where,
don't you. So, cough it up.
C'mon... I just want to see her.
Look, as I've told you before.
I haven't the faintest idea.
Not that it matters, but...
she's a virgin!
And, you know...
such a sweet girl.
You just don't find that
kind of innocence anymore.
AKA socially awkward!
She loves the fine arts.
She loves drawing jellyfish.
She's a lady,
through and through.
High priestess of otakudom.
I think... she'd be a
great wife for a politician.
A wife...
And she lives real close! In
that retro building that looks
straight outta the '20s.
Yes, I know it. The
Amamizu-kan on Block 3.
Oh wow, Mr. Diet Secretary.
You know your neighborhood!
Well, the area's being
considered for redevelop--
She forgot these when she
left. Glasses and sweats.
Go on! Take 'em
back to her, big boy!
While she's still dolled up!
I can write it down if ya
want, but her name's Tsukimi.
"Tsukimi..." "Tsukimi..."
Here we are.
Oh my! It's Kuranosuke's
dashing older brother!
Believe these are yours.
You came all this way
just to give these back?
Care to join me for some
tea? It's the least I can do!
I'll admit... I've been
hoping for a chance to
talk to you for some time.
As have I.
Noooooooooo!
Game over, vamp!
Bloodsucker, be gone!
Huh? Kuranosuke's brother?!
Didn't... Didn't I just
run past him earlier?
What's he doing here?!
You came all this way
just to drop these off?!
Thank you... you really...
shouldn't have!
Uh... those belong
to a lady named Tsukimi?
I'm told she lives here?
Yeah. That's right! Thanks
so much for dropping by!
Hey, girls! I made
us some Dokudami tea!
All right! Dokudami tea!
That's gonna hit the spot!
Here comes the snack
train! All aboard, you guys!
Also, I picked up Rakuten
Market's Number One
rated sweet,
green tea roll-cake!
Yeah! Epic om-noms!
Target lock!
Banba needs cake! Banba
needs cake! Banba needs cake!
Last one to the green
tea roll-cake's a rotten egg!
What just happened?
Say, who was that shady looking
fellow in the suit out front?
Door-to-door salesman, maybe?
What a dump.
The sooner we
tear that place down
for redevelopment,
the better.
If the flower hat
jelly's the flashy one...
the suave older
brother's none other than
our friend
Sanderia Malayensis!
Oh! What a match!
Hey, Clara? Kuranosuke
and his brother don't really
look all that related do they?
Well, Shu? How'd it go?
Mission accomplished?
The only women I
encountered there were
a bunch of creepy wackjobs.
One of 'em... had her
hair in braids, yeah?
Creepiest one of
the bunch, that one.
Damn... the magic wore off.
Be straight with me. Why do
you want to track down Lina?
I mean... your mother?
Don't worry. I'm not
gonna do anything to
make myself a political
liability. I just... wanna...
I wanna look in Mom's closet
again, like when I was a kid.
Mom... y'know how people
say that falling in love
makes a girl beautiful? Does it
mean if she never finds someone,
she'll be all grubby forever?
What about the Sisterhood?
They don't have boyfriends, but
they love Three Kingdoms stuff,
and trains, and dolls
with all of their hearts.
Today, when
his eyes met mine...
could I have been...
falling in...?
Don't even tell me
you used makeup remover,
'cause that's a damn lie!
Oh, Mom... who decided that
girls had to be pretty, anyhow?
I don't wanna be pretty!
I just wanna be me! Tsukimi!