Tsukimi!
Let's make one! You and me!
We'll take all the money
we earn... and buy this place!
Come again? Take you back
home as quickly as possible?
Sure, but what's the hurry?
I don't know what put the
idea into my father's head...
but I need to make sure
that he understands...
there's nothing between us.
Think I'll tag along.
Out of the question.
Uh, try again!
Wow! I've never
been chauffeured before!
Sugi m'man... You
dropped the ball big-time.
Yo, Clara here! This is ironic,
'cause Hanamori doesn't know
he's the one
who dropped the ball.
When you dial from
your "Recent Calls" list,
press the right one!
Uh, hey Sugi...
I can't believe I'm about to
meet the Mr. Koibuchi in person!
I'll be on my very
best behavior... of course!
What do you... hope
to accomplish by this?
Pardon me, Shu...
Traffic is light this evening.
We'll be home in
five minutes, maybe less.
Can't we...
just drive you home?
Oh, Driver! Step on it!
As you wish.
I give that bath a 9.5!
Fancy some of this,
now that you're done?
Do I ever! That's a bottle
of "Khan-tay" Shao-shing wine.
An homage to Guan Yu!
An "homage" huh? I thought
it was just regular sake.
The couple next
door's moving away...
They left this for
us as a goodbye gift.
Aw, I'll be sorry to
see them go. He was aging.
Like a bottle of fine wine.
Apparently, they bought a
little place in the suburbs.
Don't tell me those cowards
fell for the machinations of
that high-breasted she-devil!
What?! You're saying she
pressured them to sell?!
Man... jellyfish come in a
bunch of different types, huh.
Um... could you please put your
girl clothes back on... please?
C'mon, you want me
to freeze my butt off?
Yeah, they look
great, but once the
sun goes down, I'm a popsicle!
Your sweats are warm, but
boy they're tough on the eyes.
Even I look unfortunate
when I'm wearing them.
Well, change out
of them already, then.
Focus, Tsukimi. We're
looking for inspiration here.
Hey, what about...
something like this?
We start out with that
really colorful one...
We use that jelly as
the motif... and then we
bust out a skirt... y'know,
something in the same vein...
Tsukimi, why are
you freaking out?!
That sketch is a travesty!
You're repeating yourself.
That thing you drew might
as well have been a sifo-zoan
whereas the jelly from the photo
is a hydrozoan, which should be
obvious, even to an
XY-chromosome savage
such as yourself!
It has a thin bell, thin as
blown glass! And the tentacles!
They're much more slender
and delicate! They're gorgeous!
They're worlds
apart, you philistine!
They're worlds apart!
And you're still
repeating yourself...
I'm gonna show you...
how it's s'posed to look!
This is a flower hat jelly!
Gimme.
Huh?
Serious... if I saw that
in a window, I'd buy it
no matter how much it cost!
Well, I get where
you're coming from,
but they're super
delicate, so you can't
really keep these
jellies as pets.
Bathtub's free,
knock yourself out!
Oh, Fake-Boob Chick's
still up here, huh?
Sure is! But she
was just leaving!
Where are you taking me?
My place. No one'll
barge into my room.
So... That means... We're
going inside your house!
The same house as
your older brother!
Nah... I wouldn't worry
about Shu being around.
Lately, it seems like he hasn't
been home very much at all.
Think he was already
gone when I headed out.
Oh... uh... what a relief.
An' anyway... Shu doesn't
realize that "Before" Tsukimi
and "After" Tsukimi
are the same person.
Here's the deal... You stay
in the car until I'm done
speaking with my
father, understood?
The only reason you're
tormenting me with that photo
is to gain access to him,
so I'm going to play along
and introduce the two
of you. And once I have...
That's it... You're
going to leave me alone,
once and for all.
So that's all I am to you...
a blackmailing hussy...
I... didn't mean...
What are you waiting for...
if that's how you feel...
Hold on...
This is real leather, I
don't want you getting your
snot on it. Take the
handkerchief already...
I'm not kidding.
Hold on. Who's sitting
out front in the car?
W-W-Wait a sec, what
if it's your brother?
You told me he wasn't
going to be around!
Chill out.
It's Hanamori, and...
What the hell...?
Some chick?
Huh?
Uh... can I help you?
Check it out.
It's that land shark who
wants to tear
down your building...
isn't it?
You're from... Amimazu-kan!
Hanamori! Ya mind telling
me what the hell's going on?!
Why is this woman sitting
in our car?! See this coin?!.
It's gonna scrape the
hell outta the Benz's paint!
She's a friend
of your brother...
I picked them up at her place
and drove them back here.
Shu brought a girl home?
Kuranosuke!
Hold up, Bro. I
need some answers here.
Why'd you bring this
man-eater back to the house?
What--?! I can't have a guest?
Good evening.
I want to thank you for the
friendship you've shown Shu...
I'm his dad.
A pleasure to meet you...
My business card, if I may.
Sure. But I know who you are.
Please excuse my coming out
in my robe instead
of inviting you in,
but Shu insisted
we do things this way.
Of course.
Well... I guess there's no
point beating around the bush.
Miss Inari... is it true
that you and my boy...
made it to home base?
Oh my... I confess... we
have joined, in body and soul!
You chicken!
Tsukimi!
Don't go freaking out! I
don't know what she's up to,
but I do know
she's full o' crap!
Really?
He didn't get with you?!
There's no way! It's impossible!
'Cause Shu's still a--!
He's! A... um...
All ears!
'Cause he's... a virgin.
Vi-vi-vi-vi-vi-vi-vi-vi-vi!
Say it!
A virgin, huh?!
Yup.
Like... a virgin...
virgin...?!
I bet you two
haven't done jack.
I... we...!
See, Tsukimi? It's okay...
She's just trying to
play my brother. Those
two so didn't get it on.
We did it all! Back in my
neighborhood, virgins tremble
at the mere sound of my naaaame!
In Ichikawa over in Chiba,
the boys used to call me
"Shoko the Virgin Slayer!"
Man, you're so full of it!
That nickname is obviously fake.
What book did
you swipe that from?
I'm telling the truth,
dammit! Don't believe me?!
Fine! How about... some
photographic proof?!
In your face!
Tsukimi!
Oh, Mom... what's a
girl supposed to do when
she finds out something...
she really didn't want to know?
I mean, how... how do
you un-see something...
once it's burned
its way into your brain?
It's no fair. Why can't
I forget what just happened?
Just erase it completely?
Not only what happened
right now... but all of it.
Every last memory...
that he's a part of...
Please, I don't
want them anymore...
Tsukimi...
Huh?
Chilly.
Commercial message!
Clara!
Are you ready for more?!
Tequila!
Hey, Mom... Here's the plan...
I'm gonna go to sleep and forget
about all the horrible stuff.
That's my specialty, right?
Even when I was little.
Like if I had a
rough day at school...
Hey, Kurashita.
What's that book about?
Huh? It's just
jellyfish stuff?
Eww, gross! They're
all slimy and weird!
I'd walk home
all by my lonesome.
Welcome home, Tsukimi.
I'd eat the curry you
made... and then you'd slice up
an apple for dessert... and
I'd be all happy and full...
Before long... I'd snuggle
under the kotatsu blanket with
my jellyfish field
guide and fall asleep...
I dreamed about jellyfish, of
course. In my dreams, we would
float through the sea
together, my friends and I...
It felt like I was really
floating... drifting through a
world of infinite blueness...
It was so much fun...
I could have
done it forever...
I'd wake up already tucked
into bed... like magic...
Yeah... just like
when I was little...
I'll go to sleep... and
dream of a sea of jellies...
Tsukimi...
Tsukimi... Tsukimi...!
Come on girl!
Wanna be... swim-buddies?
Hi, Clara! Yeah!
C'mon, let's go!
Didja know? I'm really
good at the butterfly stroke!
Oof... Oof...
There you are...
Care to see it again?
Okay, open them! Look at this
gorgeous dress, Kuranosuke!
Your daddy gave
it to me as a gift!
The color makes it almost
look like a wedding dress, huh?
Try it on, Mama. Try it on!
Oh, honey... Only a bride should
put on something like this.
It's funny. Mama's
got so many dresses...
but that's the one
nobody's going to give her...
That's what I'm talking
about. Bravo, Tsukimi.
I really think you're
on to something here.
I almost forgot to girl it up.
Eh, just the wig.
I'm in a hurry!
How long are you gonna
scowl at me for, huh?
All I did was tell
your father the truth.
We might've...
joined in body that night...
But I still don't
believe we joined in soul.
Oh my god! I almost
choked on my coffee!
Listen to you, that's
the thing you're hung up on?!
You are a riot,
Shu, y'know that?!
Isn't the
night breeze romantic?
Would you please
stop changing the subject?
Look... You've met my
Father... now please do as
I've asked you
and leave me alone.
Can I... let you
in on a little secret
you haven't
figured out yet?
What's that?
The truth is... you like this.
You enjoy being wrapped around
the finger of a woman like me.
What? That's absurd!
If I were really such
a bother, you'd just leave.
No one's forcing you to
drink tea with me tonight.
But here you and
I sit. Because...
Deep down, in your
secret heart of hearts,
you can't wait to
get me into bed again.
Thank you for coming!
He really is a
virgin... Good lord.
Well, I can't
say I'm not relieved.
You've a lot on your plate.
I'm sorry it concerned you
in the first place.
Don't be silly.
But... this is indeed a
growing problem
in Japanese society.
Thanks to the Equal
Employment Opportunity Law
taking effect, more women are
venturing into the workplace.
Some forgoing
marriage altogether...
The number of Japanese
men who've yet to marry
has shot above 40%.
I'll sleep easy tonight...
knowing that boy of yours
got his V-card punched!
Yes. And the lady in
question is quite experienced.
The best kind to
turn a boy into a man.
It's true! Very true...
the lucky dog.
So, how would you classify
her? Club bunny? Teenybopper?
Christmas cake? Plain
Jane? Online dating type?
Raging Twitter addict?
I'll be straight with you.
Apparently, it's
that redeveloper.
Uhm... That puts... us
in a... bit of a fix, yeah?
"In a bit of a fix"
is putting it lightly...
That's why I'm
sending Shu out on a
nationwide inspection tour.
To have Hanamori investigate
the hell out of
her while he's gone.
I may as well
admit there's one more.
There's one more girl
I'm concerned about.
No way! So there's another
one?! Like father, like son!
You're such a
horndog, y'know that?!
Thank you?
Sorry to barge in, Uncle...
I didn't know you were here.
Something is different about
you. Tell me, dear Shu-Shu.
Did you finally
have some S-E-X?
Hah?!
It's no use. When I close
my eyes and try to fall asleep,
I see it all again,
shot-by-shot, like a slideshow
on the insides
of my eyelids.
It hurts a lot.
Too much to sleep.
I humbly request your wisdom!
Intruder alert! Bandit!
Highwayman! Burglar!
A thief, for reals?
Dude, I got this!
What's your cunning plan?
Cooking wine. That's
all the alcohol we've got?
Maybe I'll walk to
the convenience store.
Huh?
It's a she-burgler!
Tsukimi, you ninny! What
possessed you to burgle us?!
I raised you better than that!
Robbing the menfolk
would be one thing, but this!
This!
Wait! I wasn't burgling!
I just wanted a
little drink, okay?!
"Little drink?!" So this is
the handiwork of demon rum?!
You're an under-aged
alcoholic burglar, Tsukimi.
And that is
something I cannot abide!
I'm sorry, I couldn't
sleep and I thought a drink
or two could
help me get to bed!
Couldn't sleep, huh?!
Well, why didn't you just say?!
Drink up, young non-burglar!
And let Guan Yu's
peerless spirit cart
you off to dreamland!
Don't let the bottle play you
for a fool, though, Tsukimi!
It's just regular sake from
our cowardly ex-neighbors.
Less talking,
more drinking, ladies!
Start you off with just one.
Whoa.
Woo hoo! She's
chugging like a champ!
Man!
She was sunk by sweet sake?!
You gotta be kidding me!
C'mon. That's not
even the good stuff!
What's all the hollering about?
And for the love o' Pete.
What were my girls doing
in the middle of the hall?!
Uh... they were...
on guard duty!
Honestly, you two!
You'd better put them back
where you found them!
Ten-four, mama-san.
Tsukimi? Aw... You should
be sleeping in your bed, dear.
What am I going to do with you?
Tsukimi... Tsukimi...
Hey, Tsukimi... come on!
Hey, Clara.
Are you okay?.
It sounds like you're
getting the sniffles!
Um... my forehead
is kinda hot.
That's fine, if it
helps me get to sleep.
Because, then I'll
forget all the bad stuff.
Huh? What kind of bad stuff?
Uh... guess I forgot. I forgot
the bad stuff already, Clara!
So it's all gone?
I'm so happy for you!
Hey... now that you're
here... wanna swim to the
East China Sea with
me? It'll be fun!
Wow... it's a brood
of Japanese sea nettles!
Look at 'em all!
They're pretty, but don't forget
how poisonous they are, Tsukimi.
No touching!
Okay!
Gorgeous! Like something
a princess would wear!
How come... I feel
so warm and floaty?
This is neat!
I feel so peaceful!
Oh... I get it...
Mom must've picked me up.
She's carrying me
off to bed right now.
Oh, Mom...
Geez, you're heavy...