Time to get
baked, little dude...
Oh no. You're
in sweet potato hell!
Banba! When you bake a sweet
potato, aren't you supposed to
put it on the wood before
you light the fire? Hah?
No worries.
I'm a pro at this.
Huh?
Fro-mageddon!
Fro-mageddoooon!
Hey Mom. The Sisterhood and
I put together a little bonfire
and baked some sweet potatoes
from Dad's farm this afternoon.
Crisis averted.
For now!
That smells good.
You and me and Dad... we
used to have bonfires a bunch,
didn't we?
Yeah... like that day...
Hey, sweetie, wanna help
me gather some firewood?
Yeah!
Don't push yourself
too hard, okay?
I'll take it easy, I promise.
Lookit, Mommy! Look!
I found some driftwood. There's
a whole bunch of it over here!
I'm gonna bring
it back to Daddy,
'cause he makes
really good fires with it!
When'd you get so smart, baby?
I a'member the one Daddy
made last time! Wow, look!
That's the biggest driftwood
in the whole worl--!
Mommy...?
Another minute or two
and they should be done!
I know it was years ago,
but it feels like
it was just yesterday.
Something reminds me
of you, and I start to cry.
Days like this, I just
wanna watch the jellyfish.
The more established restaurants
and kimono fabric shops
oppose the
redevelopment plans.
That's something
to keep an eye on.
Hey, bro!
What have I told you
about barging into my room?
I broke into
the old man's room.
Come on, searching
the house again?
Yeah... But I still didn't
find Mom's address anywhere.
Sucks to be you. Holed up in
here, working on your day off...
What's this?
Oh... Redevelopment plans
for your friend's building.
Probably a high-rise hotel.
Listen up!
Hands off the starchy
carbs, girls! This is no time
for sweet potatoes!
Feast your eyes on these!
Top-secret documents! This
block is getting a facelift!
Two years from now,
it'll be a ritzy hotel!
What's this all about?
A ritzy... hotel?
Hey! I never lived
anywhere ritzy!
Right?
Oh my, yes!
Wise up! You five ain't gonna
be living in the damn hotel!
Without this building, you're
all screwed! You're a bunch of
NEETs, remember?! Who's gonna
rent apartments to you guys?!
No jobs, no references?!
Not gonna happen!
And I don't want to see
an awesomely retro place
like this bite the dust!
It shall endure! The Nunnery
must live on when all of us
are dust! God may forgive its
destruction but I never will!
Do calm down, Mayaya! It's
still in the planning stages,
and folks're already
protesting against it!
Wait, you knew, what was up?
Duh. Even we read the
neighborhood newsletter, Meat.
We do live here.
Don't cry anymore. Please,
Mayaya! Just try to remain cal--
"Better to wrong the
world than have it wrong me!"
by the brave warlord Tsao Tsao.
Don't know why I expected
a sensible response
out of any of 'em.
Could you please go home
already? Like I ask every time.
I'm heading out for a bit so
you. Should. Go. Home. Now...
You, go out?
Who'd a thunk! Shopping?
No... to an aquarium...
for the jellyfish...
Oh, I'm not busy.
I'll tag along!
Huh?! No, no you don't wanna
do that! It's like an hour away!
Y'know the Enoshima Aquarium
in Shonan? It's that one!
If we go by car we'll
be there in no time!
Let's take my brother's
Benz. Driver included!
Huh?!
We'll get ya all Cinderella'd
up, just like before!
Tsukimi, hon? Could I
grab another sweet potato?
Tip of the
iceberg, ladies!
Sick! And we can
borrow any one of 'em?!
My dear girl! I am so
glad you've awakened to
the wonders of the kimono!
Hey! This one's
got a cute pattern!
You have good eye!
That's an heirloom obi from
the early Showa period that
I discovered in this kimono
shop in Nishiogi I frequent--
It's in amazing shape
for its age, right?!
There aren't many sashes
of this pedigree and vibrance
in circulation anymore! This one
started life as a double-weave
sash but was repurposed in
the Nagoya style so it could be
worn in more casual situations.
You can pair it
up with every pattern.
Chieko, you're
kinda freaking me out!
Let's shoot for the moon and
use a collar with roses, too!
I think you should
do the honors, Chieko.
When it comes to putting
on a kimono, this boy--
♪Oh boy! Oh boy! I'm gonna
try on a kimono, dugga-dun!♪
♪Dance the Kimono Samba!
Oh boy! Oh boy, oh boy!♪
You can't keep saying
"boy" in front of them!
Okay, okay. Chill!
Now it is time to give yourself
to the kimono, body and soul!
Oh, big brother!
Do us a solid, huh?
Lend us your car?
Didn't think you and the
Benz were a package deal.
Hanamori's with Father. He's
golfing a round in Hakone.
Fore!
Excellent shot, sir.
You're on a roll today.
Yeah, whatever! You're
only chauffeuring 'cause
she's here with me.
Tsukimi...
Uh... yes...?!
The other day... when I stopped
by to return your glasses...
I'm sorry about how that went.
Huh?
I meant to hand the bag
right to you, but... well...
Then... why didn't
he hand it to me?
Of course! I was so gross
he was afraid we might
accidentally touch
or something!
Lesson time! See how
she decided she was all grody
without anyone else
telling her she was?
This is "textbook behavior"
for your typical otaku-girl!
Wait... But we're
talking and I don't even
feel like I'm gonna barf...
Tsukimi, you want some?
Is it because I'm
not wearing my glasses?
Not too shabby, eh guys?
I heard this place was
popular lately, but dang!
Uh... Tsukimi...?
Whoa... Somebody's
walking faster than usual.
Wait for us, yeah?
Come on, the jellyfish
room is this way!
Move it, slowpokes!
She's like a
whole 'nother girl.
Check out all the spotted
jellies! And they're
way teensier than Clara,
even! Aren't they just
the cutest things you've
seen in your whole life?!
Just look at how happy
she is. Her love of
nature is invigorating.
Isn't it, Kuranosuke?
She doesn't love
nature, just jellyfish!
Tsukimi...
Ground Control to Major Shu!
Uh... brother guy...
would you... mind...
standing over here for me?
What, like this?
Perfect! Don't move!
They really do look alike!
Huh?
I so called it! Your brother
is the spitting image of
Sanderia malayensis, the
prince of the jellyfish world!
I mean, your brother doesn't
have tentacles and the jelly has
no brain, but they
give off the same vibe!
Hey, um...
Yeah? What's up? Uh...
Would you mind... standing...
Over there? You're in my way.
I've never made this jelly's
acquaintance before.
Without my glasses,
I have to get real close!
No prob. I gotta pee, anyhow.
Look at me. Waltzin' straight
into the ladies' room...
Come on... why're you
letting it get to you, man?
Eeee! What're you doing
in here?! You have got
a perfectly good bathroom
of your own! What a stud!
My bad. Not payin' attention.
Don't worry. No harm done...
What the hell? Why's
she being so cute right now?
I'm seeing her have
fun for once, is that it?
Betcha that's a big part of
it. And, I don't think she's
ever actually looked at
me when we're talking before.
Why... why does
that... piss me off?
Commercial message!
Clara!
Are you ready for more?
Tequila!
All of my life, from birth
up 'til five minutes ago,
basically... I've always
had girls flock to me.
My pockets? Full of business
cards. Modeling and pop idol
agencies. Record labels. Agents
run after me on the street.
Hottest girl in school? Check.
Hottest girl at some
other school? Check.
And local beauty queens?
Oh yeah, checkity
check check check.
I was a hit with the
ladies. Too big of a hit.
Caused me a lot of woman
drama, and now I'm bored of 'em.
Popularity is for chumps.
It's a pain in the ass.
So why does this,
an awkward little hug...
between my bro, the political
dweeb with the charisma of
a sweet potato... and some
otaku girl with a head full of
jellyfish who can't
even hardly see him.
Why the hell does
it piss me off, huh?
What do I care?!
They're both nerds!
Yeah, no, don't care.
Hey, guys? Hanging on
each other in public?
Kinda tacky.
Let's wrap it up, yeah?
Get yer paws offa her!
Tsukimi, what are you crying
for? Come on what's wrong?
Aw, now your makeup is a mess!
I... I'm sorry... I'm
gonna go clean up a bit...
Well! Don't touch your
eyes unless you gotta!
Ahh, the mascara's waterproof,
guess it doesn't matter.
What was that all about?
I... I don't know...
A likely story! Remind
me how old you are?!
I'm... thirty...
The heir of a famous political
family hanging all over a girl
barely outta high
school in a public place?!
I'm calling the tabloids, perv!
Hold on! It wasn't like that.
She just started crying, okay?
Out of nowhere...
I didn't know what to do.
So I guess... I hugged her.
She said the
jellyfish reminded her.
Mama will still be
watching you... okay, baby?
Up in heaven. I'll be
watching you, every day...
Please, don't cry,
Tsukimi. I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry... These... weren't
here the last time I came...
Uh, can you tell
me what's wrong?
I shouldn't cry!
I promised her...
What?
When... my mom died... I
promised... I wouldn't cry!
It's okay. You can
cry. Let it all out.
I feel a little calmer.
Wait... What just
happened back there?!
Are you all right?
It's okay. You can
cry. Let it all out.
What? This can't be
right! According to these
thermal imaging
memories, it's as though
we were occupying
the same space!
Warmth on my back,
and shoulders and cheek
and coolness as
though his glasses!
Did the two of us... Did
Kuranosuke's brother and I...
Huh, huh...! Hug?!
He hugged me? Like, with
his arms?! On purpose?! Why?!
Of course! I was sobbing like
a baby in front of everyone.
I was disturbing the peace!
He had to take one for the team,
like a... like some kind
of "otaku whisperer!"
I like to snuggle with 'em.
Then let 'em just tucker out.
This one is especially daft!
That's so selfless of him!
You know...
bloody's not your style.
Stop freaking out! I go into
the ladies' room all the time!
Lose the gore...
wipe your face...
a little kimono
triage... and voila!
I seal thee!
It's no good.
When I can see him,
I'm too nervous
to say anything!
Tsukimi?
Oh! Uh... yeah?
Sorry. You know... about your
mom'n all... I didn't realize.
What? No. I'm the
one who's sorry for
causing such a
scene back there.
I know what it's like.
Huh?
Sucks to lose your mom.
Uh, thank you!
For driving me out to
the aquarium like you did!
I hope I didn't ruin your day or
anything! 'Kay, then! G'night!
Good! Plunking those glasses
on her transformed Tsukimi
back into her usual
awkward self. Wait a sec...
Why am I jazzed
about something like that?
Emergency! Emergency! Bona
fide crisis, coming through!
The nib of my pen's
worn down to a nuuubbbb!
What's going on?
There you are! It's
about time, young lady!
We have a situation!
Hurry into the foyer!
Ms. Mejiro got her
deadlines mixed up!
Banba! Fill in the
solid blacks on this.
Ten-four.
This hasn't been inked at all!
Banba! Your hair's
working against us!
It's going to
soak up all the ink!
Bah, nib famine! They
were sold out of my brand!
Good lord, Jiji.
Don't draw extra old men!
Just finish what's
on the page!
Whoa, you're good
at old dudes...
My poor nib-less
calligraphy pen!
You're like a
decapitated soldier...
Honestly, these girls
aren't any help at all.
Quick, go get changed
as fast as you can!
You're the last
fresh troop I've got!
Aye-aye!
What the...?! How am I supposed
to take it off? What if I untie
this part? Huh?! It's like
I'm wearing a Rubik's Cube!
Hurry, Tsukimi! Hurry!
Poor pen!
Banba knocked over the
inkwell! It's everywhere!
Nibless nub!
Okay, we do this the hard way!
Jiji's drooling over
those old men she drew!
She's totally delusional!
I give up!
Chieko! Help! I can't get
myself out of this kimono!
Hugging you... was
the height of presumption.
Please excuse my
behavior. Good night.
Really, you too?!
What's with the nosebleed?
That's really sad, Bro.
Geez... All you
two did was hug.
Hey, now. Stop the presses. Shu
was already in high school when
I moved into the mansion. We've
lived under the same roof for
a decade and change now.
But I don't think he's had
a girlfriend this whole time.
Sir... Tomorrow's front page.
How's the front?
You'd have to run
the media gauntlet, sir.
Like always. Maybe I should
cancel that dinner tonight...
What's crack-a-lackin,'
Kura-poo!
'Sup, Uncle? Hey, am
I calling at a bad time?
Dontchu worry your pretty little
head! Nine percent of 'em
still like me. It's all
good! Oh-ho-hooo yeah!
Good job, Unc. You an' Shu have
always been pretty tight, yeah?
Word!. Shu's my boy!
Have you ever heard him
talk about the women he likes
or anything? Far as I know,
he's never brought one around.
Is the fam not down
with sex in the house?
Ha! You're kiddin' me, right?
The Shu-meister's still
a virgin! It's all the rage
these days, but whatevs!
How many are left?
Tsukimi's working
on the very last one.
Trace faster, dude!
Tsukimi! You must become one
with the pen, in body and soul!
He totally saw me! Half
flopped out of the kimono with
a busted old tank top
I've had since high school!
I wasn't even wearing a bra!
Noooooooo!
Ink wave!
Tsukimi, no!
What have you done?!
Aw, Boys Love party-foul!
Grab something to
blot it with, quickly!
Banba! I'm
commandeering your afro!
Wait! Stop it! That's worse!
Tsukimi?!
Why're you screaming?!
My life! Is over!
You're white as a ghost!
Or, as they said in the '80s,
"like, majorly
pale, for sure!"
Mom... it's driving me nuts!
I mean, seriously. Am I jealous
about a... a lousy hug
between a couple of virgins?!
What the hell?!
I can't take it!