Chic!
Cool.
Alright, next! I'm on a roll!
You there! Breakfast Club!
What the heck's
your name, again?
A-Are you talking... to me?
Here, put this on!
And these capris too!
I don't--
It was plenty dry already.
These things have
more uses than just drying!
Tsukimi! In the bath, now!
Wha-- I get a makeover too?
We're all dressing up today!
You're all getting my
signature before-and-after!
So sorry! And you
came all this way...
I can't thank you enough!
It was a big help.
Thank you for returning it.
Say, are you free right now?
I owe you a drink as my
thanks for the umbrella.
So uh, might I ask why I'm the
only one still dressed the same?
No need to change! You look
great the way you are!
Really, it's just a
simple matter of framing.
Uhh... explain "framing."
Hi everyone! This is
Clara's Style Check Corner!
Here we see Chieko alongside
the "before" Sisterhood...
Surrounded by a panther,
a Three Kingdoms geek,
an Afro-headed train geek,
and a jellyfish geek.
You can tell right away
she's a traditional-dress geek!
But, presto! Can you
believe your eyes, folks?!
With Tsukimi and the
others looking all Stylish,
Chieko looks like a
celebrity who wears a kimono
just 'cause she can afford it!
There's "framing" in a nutshell!
And that's all for
Today's Style Check Corner!
You see? For all
intents and purposes,
your "before" is your "after."
Oh! How nice! Not
sure if I should feel
flattered or left out.
Don't worry about it. Next time
you'll get the full treatment.
No, no, I wasn't really
fishing for a makeover.
Okay! Who's ready for a
little "after dark teatime?"
But we... we have plenty of
dokudami tea right inside, so...
Don't be silly! I didn't get
us all gussied up for nothing!
Let me take you
to this great café.
No! Not a café!
And Number One with
a bullet on this week's
"Words that Make the
Sisterhood's Hearts Stop..."
You guessed it! "Café!"
Oh! Mayaya!
Villain! What'd you
put in my shoes?!
Untwist your panties.
They're spike heels.
What?! You spiked my
heels with leeches?!
They're all wibbly-wobbly!
That's ridiculous! Your
ankles are all wibbly-wobbly!
I'm gonna change
into normal shoes.
Yeah me too.
Nope! Wrong way!
No woman is properly armed
without her high heels!
They say "style starts
from the feet up," right?
Sure, they may hurt a
little, but you have to learn
to get used to them.
If you let the enemy
see you fall during battle,
you'll look like doofuses!
Yeah, so, you keep using words
like "enemy" and "battle."
What are you
planning to do exactly?
I told you! I'm gonna stop them
from tearing down Amamizu-kan!
"Stop them?" But how, though?
What will you do to stop them?
I haven't thought
of that part yet!
There's no plan?!
Insolent wench!
Disembowel yourself
in apology to Kong Ming!
It'll be fine, trust me! If
we all put our heads together,
I'm sure we'll come up with a
brilliant strategy in no time!
Today we prepare
for that moment!
It's like... cosplay
training for war!
Hey, Meat... You
totally just pulled that
out of your butt, didn't you?
A speech so hollow
would stun even Lü Bu!
This cannot be
easily forgiven! Hwaa!
Quiet, you! And Mama
didn't name her boy "Meat!"
"Boy?"
♪Oh boy! Got ourselves
all dressed up!♪
♪Gonna go get some tea!♪
Whatever! Just shut
up and come on!
And if you fall down, you
get right back up, got it?!
I think of "redevelopment" as
a "reexamination" of the role
we want our
precious land to play.
Though, of course, that's just
my own personal opinion on it.
I'll admit, the Amamizu
Station area is lacking some of
the features I'd
like to see there.
Exactly! There's virtually
no luxury space there at all.
'Scuse me a moment.
Take all the time you need.
Hello, Father...
Yes. I'm speaking with
that developer we discussed.
That's right. I'm just gathering
information at this point.
I apologize.
No need.
So, Mr. Koibuchi.
Do you hold your liquor?
As well as the
next man, I suppose.
But with your
position to think of,
I don't imagine you
let yourself get drunk.
After all,
you're "Koibuchi Junior,
Up-and-Coming
Politician," right?
Oh, gosh. No I'm still
just my father's flunky.
And these days,
second-gen Diet members
aren't too highly-regarded.
An' 'ere's the factions
within the ruling party
at each other's throats...
Sho bashic'ly... right
now the polillical shfere'ss
a lillel bit...
Huh? Plollickti--?
You don't look well!
My place, then?
Wow! You're like
the Buddhas of Bamiyan.
Wait, more like
Mount Hush-more!
Come on girls, try and relax.
No go, huh? Drinks
to start? Order whatever
looks good to you!
Ah, still no go?
They serve cocktails
here! Nope. No go.
It's all good, you know.
Look at yourselves up there!
You're not out of place
at all. You're fabulous!
So stop freaking
out and enjoy it.
You can simply act like
you're drinking tea back home.
But there's no
dokudami tea here!
Mayaya's sensitive to the
cold, she needs her dokudami
before she can get to sleep.
I've been getting
awful chills lately, too.
Excuse me!
Yes?
What drinks would be
good to warm us all up?
Well, milk tea with
ginger is a good choice.
Or we have several
hot dessert cocktails.
Listen to her
and her "milk tea!"
It's just hot
ginger water with
maybe a drop of cream! Stuff
gives me goose bumps anyway.
Ack! By the three kings!
Eight hundred yen?!
They're trying
to rip us off, man.
Round of the milk teas for
the table. Oh, and how about
a sampler of those
dessert cocktails too.
Uh y'know, I think I'll try
this green tea cocktail here.
This looks delicious!
Caramel par-- "par-fate?"
What is that, some ritzy
way of spelling "parfay?"
Order one and find out.
But it's so expensive.
I've got gold! The
whole night's on me girls,
so go ahead and
order anything you want!
One clubhouse sandwich
please! And one pasta with
prawns in pink sauce!
Who is this
"Bagna Càuda" person?!
Well? Tsukimi?
Oh! Um... I'll have one of these
"Margherita" pizzas, please.
Oh, goodness. Maybe that mickey
was just a touch too effective.
What a cute face.
My new wallpaper.
Whoopsie!
And say cheese!
Ugh, this lighting is
terrible! There's a shadow
right across my
face! Delete! Delete!
Kill the overhead...
this one on... Good!
Ack, no! Now it's too dark!
'Kay switch to nighttime mode...
keep my hand still,
hold my breath.
Oh no, don't you
move! Just sleep...
Sleep like the dead
kings of ancient Egypt!
Yes, yes, there's a good boy.
Now then, time to dig in.
Time to dig in!
Oh, it does taste like par-fay!
Mm-mm! Raw meat!
It's prosciutto.
There... there are
actual grains in this bread!
Oh, wow! I love it!
It's so sweet!
Oh gosh! The way she's
blowing on her drink!
It's... it's cute!
Bagna! Bagna-Bagna!
Bagna! Ban--
Whoa, the Kaiji limited
express! Ah! The Chuo Line.
Now I know where we are!
Excuse me, could we switch
to a table on the terrace?
Breathtaking...
Look! A Mitsu-501!
What a view! Mine eyes do see
the burning capital of Luoyang,
set ablaze by Dong Zhuo!
You don't say.
Yep, I knew it! They love it!
Looks like they've
finally started to rela--
The moon tonight looks...
just like a Moon Jelly.
It's almost like
we're underwater!
Dammit! That was freakin' cute!
You can't gaze all dreamily
into the night sky
with your eyes all sparkly
and say it looks
like we're underwater!
That's cheating, dammit!
Hey, whaddaya doin'?!
Quit bangin' on the stall!
I'm terribly sorry!
Ha ha ha ha!
Burn it to the ground!
Good morning!
Commercial message!
Clara!
And, we're back!
Tequila.
What's wrong?
Still trashed, honey?
Something to drink?
I have mineral water.
May I have my clothes, please.
Sparkling all right?
The bubbles used to get to me,
but on my trip to Italy
I learned to love it!
May I have my clothes please.
Look at this! It's a photo
of the trip to Paris I took
last year with my
oldest BFF, Yoko!
My clothes. May
I please have them?
Tokyo is a city with as many
stars as its people have dreams,
and as much neon light
as its people have despair,
don't you think?
Goodness, going home already?
I'm sorry if I burdened
you. Have a good night now.
Wait a minute,
you forgot your pants!
You'd forget your head
if wasn't screwed on.
You were great, by the way.
Seems we've got
amazing chemistry.
Well that's a first.
Knocked on my backside.
I have to say, it was
most gracious of you to
buy a sandwich
for Ms. Mejiro too!
It was nothing.
Luoyang Fire!
Hey, Meat! Buy me that
raw ham again anytime!
It's called prosciutto! And
stop calling me "Meat!"
I have a perfectly
good name, it's Kura--
"Kura?"
Um right! It's uh...
Sorry, it's... Kura-ko...?
Oh god! That is the
fakest-sounding name ever!
Kurako-Kurako-Haaa!
It sounds so old-world Japanese!
Sounds like a
locomotive crankin' up.
They bought it!
That's me! I'm
Kurako! Right, Tsukimi?
Oh, I wish you
could've seen it, Clara.
It was amazing tonight,
just like a moon jelly!
O-Oh God, the barf-tastic act
of talking to a jellyfish is
looking cute to
me for some reason!
I ate so much my
pants are gonna burst.
Oh! My achin' foot!
I just walked home
without my shoes.
Hey would ya
look at the time!
You're leaving?
Good night. Thanks again.
Ugh! I think I have
to burn my coolness card!
Kura-poo! Welcome home!
From Hollywood... Here's Uncle!
Hey, Unc. I didn't
know you were gonna be here.
Don't you have too much on
your plate to be visiting us?
I'm here because there's
too much on my plate!
Unless your papa
saves my sweet patootie,
I'll be in deep doo-doo!
Boo-hoo!
Kuranosuke! How many
times do I have to tell you?
Don't show your face in
front of me dressed like that!
Yeah. Sorry 'bout that!
Tastes great! Less filling!
Uncle, what are you doing?!
I'll take you to court!
No, no, Kura-poo,
you've got it all wrong!
I'm done with my private
chat with your papa,
so now it's your turn.
What?
Someone told you about
what happened to Shu-Shu?
What "happened" to him?
I mean, that is why you called
me the other day, right?
Fishing for dirt on
his history with women?
Nah, I just figured
you might know something
about his seeming
lack of love life.
Hey, would you
look at the time...
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
You can't start that story
and just leave. Finish it!
Ah! Oh, Kura-poo! Naughty boy!
Now no one will want me...
Get back here, Baldy!
Oh! My poor virgin eyes!
I'll never be the same!
Dammit! Where'd he go?!
Uh, brother dear?
Wow get a load of you!
You're like a chick in a bad
TV movie who just got molested!
"Molested?"
Crap! He's gettin' away!
Is that it? Have I
just been... molested?
Hanamori! I need the car--!
No touching!
Right! Right, sorry,
I see that you're waxing.
Which means...
This needs ten full hours
to dry. It's quite impossible
for me to take you
anywhere right now.
Cryin' out loud!
Hey, Uncle, why'd
you run away, huh?!
Finish your story!
Spill the beans already!
I'll never get
to sleep like this!
I tried to get Hanamori to
go after you in the car, y'know!
Seriously! Huh?
Hanamori? Yeah, he's here.
Hanamori...
No touching.
Uncle just told me if I
wanted to know why Shu's got
such a phobia of women,
I should ask you about it.
There are some things...
you're just better
off not knowing.
That's a load of
crap and you know it!
If you don't tell, I'll
plaster my hands all over
your shiny, shiny hood! Eh?
There is a perfectly good
reason for Shu's woman phobia.
Whoa, not even one second!
It all stems back to something
that happened 21 years ago,
when he was only nine.
Your father took Shu to
the theater to
see a musical...
Where he saw your father... and
your mother, Lina... Together.
Hanamori? I know it's late.
Could you run me somewhere?
It won't come off! No matter
how many times I wash my face
and my hair, this
stuff won't come off!
Good grief. Sounds like
we're out of soap and shampoo.
Tsukimi, could you run
to the Iwahashi drug store
and pick up some more?
Roger!
Be back in a few, ladies!
I'm sorry to come so
late, and dressed like this.
Could I ask you
to shake my hand?
Thank you for your time.
Sorry again for the
hour. Have a good night.
What? Wait, what?!
Shu, I'm afraid I've messed up.
I told Kuranosuke
about your trauma.
I'm sorry. I found myself
in an impossible predicament...
Uh, oh, I see. Okay.
Well, I suppose you have
always had your... weakness.
I am sorry.
Father! Father, where
did you go? We have to
hurry back home...
Mother is waiting for us!
She said we have
to come home early,
'cause we're having
sukiyaki for dinner.
It's your favorite.
Father?
That's some... heavy stuff.
Oh no, we didn't do anything...
But he thinks we did.
Hook, line n' sinker!
Yeah no, it's perfect.
Pictures, the whole nine!
He was so flustered that
he left something behind,
so when I go return it,
I'll use my rad moves
and wrap him
'round my finger.
What? My slang is
too dated? The 80's?!
'Nother crack like
that and you're toast!
What... just happened...?