Good morning, everyone.
Saku-rako, Midori-ko, O-Chiyo,
Matsuko, O-Take,
Umeko, Yoshibo...
You're all looking
as lovely as ever.
Good morning!
Hey Chieko, would
you do me a favor?
You're certainly
here early this morning.
Well... I just have way
too much on my plate today.
That's why I'm here...
to pick up that thing.
Ahh, "that thing..."
All right, I'll let you play,
but promise you'll be nice.
Not the dolls. I meant
that thing over there.
The machine?
Oh, that's right. I stayed
up late drinking sake in
the kitchen last night... And
then... Mom carried me to bed.
A dream?
Hey Mom, guess what? Had
a dream about you last night.
But if that was a dream, how
did I get back to my own room?
I don't remember that at all.
You're up early
this morning, Tsukimi!
Hey. Yeah, g'morning.
Got two words for you
last night. Rock Star.
That brings up a good
question. Do rock stars usually
not remember how they
got back to their room?
Oh wow! The sake gods were
pleased with your drinking.
That's why they carried
you safely back to your room!
That elixir of Guan
Yu's is magic sauce.
That's not what I--
What are you doing?!
Come on, no worries.
I took Home Ec...
'Course I took
it in fifth grade.
I'm telling you, I've
had this machine for years.
I'm the only one who
knows how to use it right.
'Kay now this thing?
I think it goes here...
Don't do that.
You're going to get the
thread completely tangled.
It got all tangled.
I told you!
Hey. What're you
guys doing in here?
Tsukimi! Stop her...
She's completely off her nut!
Oh... you're awake.
Is your fever any better?
Fever?
Oh, that's right, I was
a little sick last night.
Wait, but how does he know?
Technology! Let's
start over here.
I bought all this as
soon as I got up. Look!
Fabric! Rhinestones!
And lace and beads!
O-kay...
Come on, let's do it!
Let's do what? I'm lost.
Cryin' out loud! I told you,
we're going to make this!
You want to make
a jelly? A flower hat?
Hel-lo?! The dress!
You know, I drew
that back in high school.
It's really not all that great.
I know that... but it
looks like a cool dress to me.
If we make something that
looks like this, it'll sell.
It's too cute not to! We'll
take over the fashion world!
We'll save Amamizu-kan!
I want to make this...
out of this, right here.
And I want Chieko to do it.
Sorry... I can only
make traditional clothing.
And I only use this
machine to stitch yukata.
Yukata... You made that, too?
Whoa! Chieko... you rock!
You're so sweet but anyone could
do it, it's nothing special.
How do you do it?
It's really very
easy. I'll show you.
Watch, I just started
making a new kimono for
Midoriko this morning and
I'm nearly finished with it.
So fast!
The type of stitching used
in traditional clothing is
refined from a technique
passed down in Japan
since ancient times, exclusively
using straight lines.
Western-style clothing is
all curved lines designed to
accommodate the
wearer's body shape,
it's completely different,
even on a conceptual level.
You're sewing without
even looking at your hands!
Come on, I know
you can do this!
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no!
Why not?
I already told you, Japanese
and Western sewing come from
completely different
schools of thought.
Skills don't matter if they're
in a different discipline.
I'll give you an analogy,
it's like you're asking
a sushi chef from
Tokyo to make a fine roux
like a French chef in Paris
would. It can't be done.
You're a sewing
savant, don't you see?!
The point is, I can't possibly
make something so complicated.
If I help, it'll only
be with stitching.
You'll just have to make the
rest of it work yourselves.
"Make it work," she says...
And that's all I have
for the moment regarding
our Hotel Createur
Tokyo. Let's move on now to
the situation with the
west side of Amamizu Station,
where construction is
planned. We are in continuing
negotiations with the residents
so that we can break ground
the year after next at the
latest. The site purchase is
proceeding on schedule
and shouldn't encounter any
major delays as the project goes
forward over the coming months.
That's no good. Amamizu-kan
is right in the middle of the
proposed site. What'll Tsukimi
do once the buyout is final?
What? I'm evicted?
Yes... unfortunately.
But where will I
live? It's my home.
I've got nowhere else to go!
It'll be all right, Tsukimi.
We can make a home together!
Together?
We can rent a little
house by the shore.
We'll live a humble,
quiet life together
just watching the jellyfish.
That'll never happen.
Y'see... she won't forgive
you having sex with me.
I'm sorry!
Tsukimi Kurashita, huh.
Mhm. Mr. Koibuchi insisted.
Shu's gone... he leaves
tonight to go overseas...
so he won't find out.
So you don't got a photo?
How about an address?
H-How many
meters did you buy?
I don't know, I just
bought the whole bolt.
Let's cut the sucker up.
Are you sure that's
the right way to start?
No clue. But we've
gotta start somewhere.
But isn't cutting a little
permanent? Just because you're
a Stylish, doesn't mean
you know how to make clothes.
Well no, but I wear
them all the time.
Banzai!
Fabric faceplant!
Iketani!
Look I'm a salmon roll or...
Raise a white flag for
Ma Chao! It is useless to
fight Liu Bei's army if
Ma Chao fights with them!
Do not get in our way! Special
Attack: "Take money and go eat!"
Ichiyo Higuchi!
We're going to Chinatown!
The Minatomirai Line is mine!
It's Chinatown, Jake!
And extra batteries!
So... where were we?
Now... Scissors!
I-I don't--
It doesn't have to be exact.
Just cut around me...
try to make it
somewhat dress-shaped.
If it doesn't work, try again.
Okay, Mom. What is
it that makes me think
this strange guy is so
beautiful? Maybe it's because
his arms and legs
are so pale and slender.
He's just like a jellyfish.
Make it like
that whatsit-jelly.
It's called a
"Flower Hat Jelly."
Yeah, that.
Looking at this beautiful young
man... he fills my heart with...
I don't know... like my heart
is filled with jellyfish lace...
It's almost enough
to make me forget
all the bad things
that have happened.
Good afternoon!
Hello.
What're you up to after this?
Back to the office.
I have to write up all the
details from the meeting.
Where're we going?
Get out of the car.
Let's go to--
Please get out!
What exactly do
you want from me?!
I get it now. So I was no more
than a one-night stand for you.
Have it your way.
If that's what you want...
I'll just disappear... forever.
Elite Man Snaring Techniques,
Inari-Style:
A Beginners' Course.
If pushing doesn't work, try
guilt ridden pulling him along.
I guarantee he'll call
in the next two or three days.
Please don't go.
That was fast! Guess I should
expect as much from a virgin.
He's got the resolve
of a middle schooler.
But watch how I
boldly ignore him.
Taxi!
No wait! Please!
Commercial message!
Clara!
Now the other part!
Tequila.
Down to 5 hundred 35 yen?
Dang, Madam Ichiyo didn't even
last us half the day.
That's because you insisted we
have the mango flan for dessert.
Right... Let's pay our respects
to the spirit of Guan Yu...
then get squeaky
clean at the public bath.
How cool!
That afro is totally righteous.
It's like, the way
biggest I've ever seen.
Do you mind if I touch it?
Omigod I already am touching it!
It's a Stylish!
Picture time... smile!
Listen up, you two.
There's no reason to try
and spare your feelings on
this. You've killed any chance
of quality work
from this fabric... ever.
No need to cut us
down right when we're
beginning to get
motivated. That's not cool.
Well... let me
see what I can do...
She's still breaking
the sound barrier!
I'll put some elastic in...
Yuck... How dare you
give my haute couture skirt
an elastic waistband?!
Hush now... Just
try it on this way.
Really?
This spring... Rock the "poor
pauper" look in a dorky skirt
with an elastic waistband!
No! Nooo!
It should be way flouncier!
With the pattern you cut...
there's no way it could be!
Oh, man...
It's wrong! That pathetic piece
of cloth isn't even close to
expressing an inch
of the delicate beauty
of the Flower Hat Jelly!
Not even a micrometer or
nanometer of the awesomeness!
My god... The otaku girl
rant has been unleashed.
To start with, the bells
of all jellyfish, not just
the Flower Hat Jelly,
contain a fluidity of
motion requisite to
their body structure.
If that's what you want,
I'll just disappear.
I'm sorry. I can't come
to the phone right now.
Tsukimi. What are--?
Mm, please just stay still.
Jeez, at least say sorry!
Careful... go slow.
It's okay. Just let her be.
There, it's finished.
At least it looks a little
bit more like a bell now.
Hey, you're right. Not bad.
Chieko, could you sew
it on the machine for me?
No problem. But what do you
want me to do with the edges?
All your margins
on the outside.
I really don't care. Long
as it's shaped like a bell,
that's good enough for me.
It's a good start, but I don't
think it'll get that shape
unless I wear
a pannier underneath.
Pa... what?
"Pannier..." That thing
all the Goth-Lolis wear
under their skirts... Y'know,
like a ballerina's tutu.
Sure... I knew that.
Oh hey, let's go
finish this at my place.
I've got a bunch
there. My bro's gone.
And there's no one else
to interrupt us. It's perfect.
O-kay...
Tsukimi?
Chieko?
Yes?
You like all
sorts of old stuff.
How'd you like to
take a bunch of pictures
of a cool old mansion?
Actually, I love old houses.
I recently went to a
Western-style
house in Kamakura...
Look.
Wow!
Could I ask you
for one more favor?
Perfect, thanks! This
is totes going on my blog.
Buh... Blog?
Afros are just so scrunchy.
Where did you get yours done?
Ah-oh-yama? It was, huh?
Uhh... I was born this way.
I've always thought
they were totally retro cool.
But my agency
won't let me get one!
One more feel
please? It's so animal!
So this is it. Not such
a bad place, I guess.
Excuse me, sir! Do you know
where I can find this address?
Uhh... that place, huh?
Dang... Why do those guys always
make me drink so damn much?
And who the hell orders
Dom Pérignon Rosé these days?!
Twelve messages...
What's a girl to do?
Wow, this salami's good.
It's ringing again!
I'm not here...
but I'll answer... speak.
Hi, it's Shu--Koibuchi.
I believe I said I wouldn't
talk to you anymore, didn't I?
Well, yeah,
but I just thought.
Oh crap.
Excuse me?
I've had too much.
My head's all fuzzy...
It's getting dark.
I'm over. Nice knowing you.
What's that? Too much
what? Talk to me... Hello?
What have you--? You didn't go
and do anything stupid did you?
I'll be right there.
What a dork. He's gotta be
joking. As if I'd kill myself
because I couldn't
have Mr. Promise Keeper.
Virgins are such
a pain in the ass.
Oh! Taisho Romance!
Jackpot! It's
a treasure trove!
I told you we had
a crap-ton of pictures of
old dead dudes
hanging everywhere.
Now are you ready to
come out of your shell
and help me with the
dress? We can do this.
Talk to me.
Please let me go home.
Why are you being so silly? My
brother's not here. I told you.
It's not him... it's--
I don't like the way I feel...
I get all heated
up over stuff and then
I go cold all of a sudden...
I'm sick of it.
Too confusing.
I want my life
just to be lukewarm.
Okay, here it is... I want
to take this jellyfish you drew
and make it real...
I want to see that... got it?
But why?
It's beautiful.
I am truly impressed!
And look...
another picture perfect room.
It's wonderful!
Be careful.
I'm so sorry! I
got over-excited...
That's okay. It's totally
cute, right? I love it.
This room is divine! I wish I'd
brought Midoriko and the others!
I wonder... If I could somehow
give the feeling of that moment
in life, not just in a drawing,
but also in real life...
a shape, with
my own two hands...
Hey, Tsuki...
Jiji... Chieko...
Lend me your aid!
No!
Psych! In your face!
Were you scared?
'Cause these are
just my vitamins.
What?
Ow, hey, stop it! Ow, ah ow! Ah!
It was just a stupid joke
there's no reason to freak--
Wow hey, that
was awfully quick.
I, guess she was
dead. Your getaway car.
Take me to the
airport, please.
Skippin' town entirely?
Let's go. Now.
Yessir.
She wasn't dead, thank god.
I'm finished over here.
Okay, what about
over on this side?
Oh boy... I fell asleep.
These pearls are
beautiful, though, aren't they?
They're fakes but
they're high quality fakes.
I think I want a
little more down here.
That's... whoa...
All done.
We finally finished! The
day is saved thanks to...
The Sisterhood
Human Wave Attack!
Fine detail work always
gets to my shoulders!
I could get the Kita no Kuni
Kara DVD box set as my reward.
Oh my god, hot!
Yeah... the
Flower Hat Jelly's the
pop idol of
the jellyfish world.
I think the tentacles
came out really nicely, too.
Hey... can I... try it on?
Oh, yeah. Tsukimi
tore apart the necklace.
But uh, they are fakes, right?
Yeah no, they're real.
Probably worth a few million...
What?! Then each pearl
is at least ten thousand?!
I'm so sorry I broke
your necklace. I just--
I thought they looked perfect
for a jellyfish's tentacles
especially the ones on
a Flower Hat. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sure it would make
my mom happy to see this...
She always
loved pretty dresses.
Mama... What if...
What if I were a girl?
I'll give you these, too...
I got them from your
papa a long time ago.
Yeah?
Sometimes I really
wish you were a girl.
Then your Papa
would understand better.
If only I'd been born as
the perfect little princess.
Maybe... maybe then I could
have stayed with my mom forever.
Never expected
we'd stay out all night.
Your fault again for not getting
out of the electric bath
in time for the last train.
Sorry! I just kinda figured
shock therapy would be
the best way to zap away
any Stylish juice
that got on us. Huh?
What's goin' on?
It's over! Baidi's been
conquered. It can't be!