(Usagi) Yay! It's
festival time!
(Chibi‐Usa) Usagi, that
lady over there...
(Usagi) Okonomiyaki, yakisoba,
shaved ice!
(Chibi‐Usa) Doesn't she look
like she's hiding something?
(Usagi) Sausages,
chocolate‐covered bananas!
(Chibi‐Usa) Are you even
listening to me?!
(Usagi)
Hey! Stop interrupting my
fun, or else...
In the name
of the moon...
(Both) We'll punish you!
"Juban Holiday: The Carefree
Princess."
And up next, the latest news
regarding the princess.
(Newscaster) Princess Rubina of
the Kingdom of Amethyst, who is
currently visiting Japan,
(Newscaster) was seen by a
doctor due to a cold.
Because of this, her previously
scheduled factory visitation and
reception have been postponed
until further notice.
How unfortunate.
Yes, indeed.
Actually, in the future, King
Endymion and Neo Queen Serenity
would also become ill when they
had royal ceremonies to attend.
Huh?
But thankfully, they both seem
to feel completely better by the
time the ceremonies are over,
so there's nothing to worry
about!
You said the King
gets sick too?
Yes.
I'd expect that from the Queen,
but the King too?
You look like you're worried
about something.
[Groans] That's because I am.
Chibi‐Usa!
Yeah...no.
(Usagi) Come on!
Don't think so!
(Usagi) You're heartless!
(Chibi‐Usa) The insults
aren't helping, you know.
And you're really not gonna help
me out with these at all?
And why should I do that?
You're the one who went on a
spending spree and blew your
allowance in a day.
(Chibi‐Usa) And now you have to
run errands for Mommy to earn a
little cash.
Duh, why else would I be doing
this? But I have way too much to
carry now.
I was hoping you'd help
with at least one.
I'll do it if you give
me half the money.
[Groans]
You don't need half of it, you
still have plenty of money!
Of course I do!
So then take one of these
bags, you greedy brat!
No way! No way! No way!
Hold it for me!
No! No! No! Hold it for me!
[Groans]
Proper girls shouldn't be
fighting like this. It's
unladylike.
Here, I can fix this.
Excuse me sir, would you carry
this young lady's bags?
[Groans]
And you can help her as well.
[Gasps]
Uh, that's not necessary!
[Chuckles] Bye‐bye! Keep up
Chibi‐Usa.
Oh.
What was that about?
Beats me.
Wow! A festival! Let's hurry
home and get changed so we can
come back!
[Groans] Guess I'm carrying all
these bags myself!
(Usagi) Ow, my arm, it's
cutting off my circulation.
[Gasps] Oh! This looks so fun!
Oh.
(Hawk's Eye) I hear she's a real
princess.
(Hawk's Eye) It's hard to
believe you let this one slip
by, Tiger's Eye.
She's a bit old for me. Besides,
from what I've heard she's
bedridden from a cold.
What? You really believe
those rumors?
You're so gullible. That's
totally just a bad cover up
story.
I'm tired of having to go to so
many boring royal events!
What do we do? The Princess has
run off without a trace!
Just tell the press that she's
come down with a cold and go
find her right this instant!
(Both) Get it?
It's so obvious.
Hmph. Whatever. She's
still too old.
Pass!
Uh‐huh.
Hmm?
(Chibi‐Usa) Come on, Usagi,
hurry up! Let's go, you slow
poke!
(Usagi) Okay, okay I'm ready!
Oh, hi.
Uh, hello, can I help you?
Why hello there. How do you do?
My name is Rubina.
Oh! It's a pleasure to meet
you! I'm Usagi Tsukino.
And I'm Chibi‐Usa!
Well?
(Both) Well, what?
Don't let me get in your way.
Feel free to continue. [Giggles]
Huh?
Well, go on!
Okay, I guess we should start
making our way to the festival
then?
Sure, let's go.
(Usagi) Don't know how you found
our house, but nice talking to
you!
Wait, isn't that?
Oh.
Oh!
Ah! Wonderful!
I love everything about this!
(Rubina) Wow!
And you said this type of
cotton is actually edible?
Uh‐huh.
Oh?
Miss Rubina definitely doesn't
seem like your normal, every day
tourist.
Yeah. Guess we'll just
have to keep an eye on
her while she's here.
Maybe if we're around
her long enough, we'll
figure out what's going on.
(Usagi) Hey! I finally did it!
Oh.
That was my
fifth try!
So this is what wasting money
looks like. I feel so informed.
[Sighs]
[Gasps] Miss Rubina is gone!
Huh? Where do you
think she ran off to?
I donno!
We should probably
find her quickly!
(Child) Mom, buy it
for me!
(Mom) No!
I want it right now!
No way.
You can do it
little guy!
I! Want! It!
(Mom) Stop acting
so spoiled!
(Nanny) You mustn't act so
spoiled, Princess.
I assure you that
I am not!
Ordinary women from other
countries are able to freely go
out and about, so why can't I?
The Amethyst Princess should
think more about the good of her
people, not her own selfish
desires.
You have to understand that for
this country and our Kingdom to
build good relations, you must‐‐
So to accomplish that, are you
saying it's perfectly fine to
simply sacrifice my freedom?
That's not what
I meant.
Princess Rubina...
[Sighs] I understand I'll get
myself ready. You may leave now.
Of course.
Buy! Me! One! Right! Now!
Here.
Uh.
[Laughing]
Hey, where are you going? That's
not yours, give it back!
Freedom, huh?
Huh?
Would you like
a balloon, too?
Mhm.
[Chuckles]
(Rubina) Here you go!
(Rubina) Oh, you want one too?
Okay!
[Chuckles]
You kids have money?
Um.
[Giggles] All right, one at a
time now.
Get back here!
[Sighs]
(Rubina) It looks so
free up there.
[Kids yelling]
Hey, Miss. 'Scuse me. You do
plan on paying for all those
balloons you gave away, right?
Oh, right.
Here.
Huh?
Hm!
Uh. Hey! I'm not in the mood to
play games here lady!
Oh!
[Screams]
(Balloon Vendor) What are you
crazy? You can't just give away
my merchandise without paying
for it!
(Balloon Vendor) Can't you see
I'm trying to run a business
here?!
(Rubina) Can you please talk a
little slower, sir?
Listen. You
better quit messing with me.
This isn't funny anymore!
(Balloon Vendor) Huh?
Huh.
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
You okay?
Oh, yes.
Here in the real world, you tend
to need a little thing called
money to purchase the things you
want...Princess Rubina.
[Gasp]
Hm.
Ah!
You were sent here to take me
back to that place, weren't you?
No, you're wrong!
Just like those balloons, I can
go wherever I please!
[Cheering]
Farewell!
Miss Rubina!
[Grunts] I won't
let you get away.
[Grunts]
You're gonna pay for those
balloons, got it?
[Chuckling] Well, aren't you a
rough one. Here.
Keep the change.
[Grunts]
Not enough!
Oh, my bad. [Sighs]
Miss Rubina!
Where do you
think she could have gone?
Hmm.
[Sighs]
Look, that's her.
Are you sure she's
really Princess Rubina?
It's hard to tell
from over here.
Huh?
Who's there?
I'm not chasing you.
So don't worry.
Oh.
Once you've had your fun, you
should probably return to your
hotel, don't you think?
Huh?
I know that freedom is still new
and fascinating for you,
but have you ever stopped to
think about how the people who
care about you must feel right
now?
I'm sure that they're all
worried sick wondering where you
are.
Who are you?
(Usagi) [Gasps] There she is!
Yay! We found you!
Huh? Mamo?
Hey.
We were actually gonna
come get you in a little bit.
The fireworks are
about to start soon!
Sorry, but I have some things
that I need to take care of
today.
Huh?
Is he a friend
of yours, Usagi?
Yeah, but much more importantly,
why did you just run off?
If there's something wrong, then
you should tell us so we can
help you.
Usagi, sometimes people have
things bothering them that they
would rather not talk about.
Don't be so forward about asking
her to tell you.
Excuse me? I bet you got that
from reading one of Mom's
self‐help books again, didn't
you?
Anyway, Mamo, why are you here
with Miss Rubina?
Oh! Yeah, why?
I just happened to run into her
as I was looking for the both of
you.
She stopped me to ask for
directions. Isn't that right?
Uh, yes!
(Usagi) I see.
I gotta run. My treat next
time. Anything you want!
Anything?! You really mean it?
Yeah.
Score!
Mamo, you shouldn't
reward children when
they don't actually
deserve it.
Well, I guess you do have a
point there. You know, it's a
good thing you're so mature,
Chibi‐Usa.
[Fighting]
Oh, Mr. Mamo...
So how'd it go?
I'm almost positive she's the
real princess.
In that case, is it okay for her
to be out with them?
I can't help but worry.
Don't sweat it. I'm sure she'll
go back eventually.
(Artemis) Oh, uh, that's
not what I meant.
I'm concerned that she's with
Usagi.
What if being around Usagi all
day makes her assume that's what
all common people are like.
[Groans]
Oh, uh, it'll be fine.
[Excited Chatter]
Wow, so cool!
Usagi?
Yeah?
I've been wondering, since he's
your friend, do you get to see
Mr. Mamo whenever you want?
Well, yeah, except for when he's
super busy and doesn't have the
time.
Hmm. Oh I see. That's wonderful.
[Cheers]
Oh wow! Pretty!
Hey! I bet we
can get even closer!
Wanna come too,
Miss Rubina?
Sure!
Let's go!
(Hawk's Eye) No amount of lights
in the night sky, can compare to
your beauty.
[Giggling] Miss Rubina!
[Gasps]
So, are you here to take me back
then? I've already decided to
return to the hotel once the
fireworks are over.
[Chuckling] But will you make it
back safely?
[Gasps]
One!
Two!
[Screams]
Three.
[Gasps] That was...
Miss Rubina!
Oh no!
Who are you?
Please forgive my rudeness,
princess. But I have an
important mission I need to
complete. Be right back.
Ah!
Where is Pegasus?
[Screams]
[Gasps]
(Usagi/Chibi‐Usa)
Moon Crisis Make Up!
[Groans]
Ugh! Are you kidding I even
wasted money on you!
(Hawk's Eye) I'll take your life
as collateral!
(Both) Hold it right there!
During a beautiful night
full of fireworks...
Only a villain would
ruin the moment!
We're the Pretty Guardians!
Who fight for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name of the Moon!
(Both) We'll punish you!
You two, again. Well I sure hope
you're here to reimburse me for
those balloons!
Come forth, my Lemures! Ms.
Elephanko, the Ball‐Riding
Elephant Trainer!
[Groans]
[Howls]
[Giggling]
I'm Elephanko, the Elephant
Trainer!
I actually owe you for what you
did to my older brother‐in‐law,
Gomumario. Remember him?
Uh‐huh. Kind of.
To be completely honest, the two
of us never really got along, so
when I heard that he went Stage
Out,
it was like a weight had been
lifted from my shoulders. I was
so relieved, do you know what
I'm saying?
Alright. I'm leaving the
rest to you, then.
(Elephanko) And of course,
despite that, he had the
audacity to keep bragging
about how great he was.
(Elephanko) It got to the
point where the whole
family hated him.
Hello?!
(Elephanko) ...he looked like
such a cream puff!
But less about him and more
about Pooko the Balloon Lady.
Oh, the things I could tell you
about her!
Hurry up and finish
the job!
[Grunts]
Fine. Then I guess it's time to
show you my special ability.
See? An elephant can't even
break me! Hmph.
So cool!
[Chuckling/Grunting]
Will you get off?!
[Grunts]
Prepare to die!
Careful, Chibi Moon!
Right.
[Laughing]
[Screams]
And just where do you think
you're going, huh?
[Screams]
I'll leave the rest to you.
Hmph!
[Grunts] Hey, what are you
doing? Would you just get your
hide in there already! You big
butt!
[Elephanko Laughing]
[Laughing] Is she the next
victim?
[Screaming]
[Laughing] If you keep running
like that, then you'll just run
that girl over!
(Both) Miss Rubina! Please! You
have to wake up!
[Laughing] That poor, little
thing!
Miss Rubina!
(Mamoru) A lovely young lady‐‐
What the?! [Grunts]
(Both) Tuxedo Mask, you're
finally here!
[Laughing]
[Pained Yell]
[Grunts]
Do it!
(Both) Right...
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Now you've gone and done it!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Wait, is it Stage Out already?
[Groans]
(Rubina) Right here is fine.
(Usagi) Huh? Are you sure?
My hotel is close by, so I'll
walk the rest of the way.
Thank you. All of you. I really
mean it. I had a wonderful time.
I'll forever cherish the
memories I made today.
Oh, Miss Rubina, you're being a
bit overdramatic, aren't you?
Come visit us again, okay?
Yes I will. Thanks again.
Good luck to you.
Hmm.
(Usagi/Chibi‐Usa) Goodbye!
(Usagi) Mako, please be careful.
(Usagi) That dance may have been
incredible, but the man you were
dancing with isn't the kind of
person you think he is.
(Usagi) He's trouble!
(Chibi‐Usa) We saw him asking a
lot of other girls out. He's not
your Prince Charming, so don't
let him fool you, Mako!
(Usagi) The last thing we want
is to see you looking hurt,
Mako. Okay?
(Usagi) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS, "Destined Partners?
Makoto's Innocence."
(Usagi) The moonlight is a
messenger of love.