(Chibi‐Moon) Helios!
[light breathing]
(Queen Nehalennia) You of the
White Moon...
His pain is nothing compared to
the humiliation your people put
me through.
And for that I am going to cast
a curse on you that will make
you sleep forever.
[laughing]
[screaming]
[chuckles]
[heavy breathing]
Helios, no!
(Chibi‐Moon) Helios!
Leave him alone!
Stop it! Stop!
[groans]
[laughing]
The Golden Crystal, at last it
is mine!
[laughing]
The seal has been broken!
Now, for the world! [chuckles]
(Usagi) "When the Crystal
Shines: The Beautiful Power of
Dreams."
Chibi‐Moon...Chibi‐Moon!
(Queen Nehalennia) The girl is
under my curse. She will never
wake up again.
Who's there? [gasps]
I don't see anyone!
Stay alert, girls!
[gasps]
[screams]
Jupiter!
Oak Evolution!
(Queen Nehalennia) [Laughing]
[gasps]
Who are you?
I am Nehalennia, the true Queen
of the Moon.
Nehalennia...
(Queen Nehalennia) And as of
today, I am also the Queen of
this world.
Hah! Yeah, right!
So you're this boss of the Dead
Moon we've heard so much about!
Why are you doing all of these
horrible things?
You and your people will never
be able to comprehend the
endless suffering...
I had to endure, while being
sealed away in that prison.
(Queen Nehalennia) But at least
I can make the people of Earth
suffer too.
Even more than I did.
I will enshroud this whole world
in darkness.
[chuckles]
Not if we have anything to say
about it!
[chuckles]
So many circus tents have
appeared.
(Mamoru) Usako!
[gasps]
Chibi‐Usa...everyone. [grunting]
Mamoru.
What is it?
[grunting in agony]
(Queen Nehalennia) Hah!
[screams]
Sailor Moon!
She'll pay for that!
Venus!
Love and Beauty Shock!
No way!
Mercury!
Aqua Rhapsody!
Mars!
Flame Sniper!
Nothing?
[gasps]
Don't you see? Now that I have
finally escaped from my
prison...
I am the most powerful being in
this world, as well as the most
beautiful!
(Queen Nehalennia) Now, people
of the White Moon, kneel before
me!
Good luck with that, you'll have
to kill us first! Right, girls?
(Sailor Venus) Oh yeah! Darn
right!
Hmph. Hah!
[screams]
[laughing]
Oh man!
Hey, check it out. Looks like
Nehalennia got the Golden
Crystal.
The Sailor Guardians are done
for unless we do something.
If we could just get that
crystal away from her.
But how are we gonna do that
without our magic?
You know, I've been wondering
about that.
Maybe we can use magic even
without our Amazon Stones.
Come to think of it...
Didn't Nehalennia say that the
Dead Moon's power originally
came from our energy?
Well?
Sure! Let's try it! After all,
we've got nothing to lose.
[laughing] Had enough of my
power?
[light breathing]
[emotional breaths]
[laughing]
[inhales]
I can't give up!
We can't lose this fight! We
won't!
[grunting]
[grunts]
Hmm.
Let's do it, everyone!
Sailor Planet Attack!
[gasps] Did we get her?
You've got to be kidding me.
(Queen Nehalennia) [Laughing] Is
that the best you can do?
[laughing]
Mamo, what do we do now?
[grunting]
He's getting worse.
Mamoru...
(Helios) My Prince...Prince
Endymion.
Who is that talking?
[sighing]
[gasps]
Why does all this look so
familiar to me?
I feel like I know this place.
(Helios) You should, Prince
Endymion.
(Helios) Your people have always
protected this sanctuary.
This place, Elysion, is where
your kingdom, the Golden
Kingdom, once stood.
[grunts]
[gasps]
Who are you?
I am, Sir...
I am Helios, the protector of
the Golden Crystal here in this
sacred land called Elysion.
I recognize your voice.
You're the one that's been
helping me and the Sailor
Guardians all this time.
(Prince Endymion) You're
Pegasus, aren't you?
I am sorry, my Prince.
Hmm?
I am supposed to be its
protector, and yet I failed to
protect the Golden Crystal.
(Helios) As a result...
This planet and your body were
both ravaged by the darkness of
the enemy's curse.
This place is maintained by
the power of the dreams of
the people of Earth.
Is that right?
Yes, but even that has come to
an end. I was unable to protect
people's precious dreams.
And now because of my failure
and the success of the Dead
Moon...
people will soon lose the
ability to dream any dreams at
all.
Are you sure?
For all of Dead Moon's
successes...
do you really think it's
possible for them to take away
people's power to dream?
For that matter, is anyone ever
truly capable of taking away
another's dream?
Huh?
(Prince Endymion) Regardless of
how dark things get...
people's dreams will always
grow, like a flower of hope in
the world.
Something that can't be stolen
away, no matter how hard you
try.
Isn't that what dreams
are all about?
Huh.
Helios.
Why do you think it is that
you've tried so hard to protect
people's dreams all this time?
Because, well, because it is my
duty.
Is that all?
No. It's because I love dreams.
I love beautiful dreams and the
people who possess them. And my
dream is to protect them all.
Exactly. And have you lost that
dream?
No, sir. Never.
(Queen Nehalennia) Hah!
[screams]
[grunts]
And now, people of the White
Moon, as much as I've enjoyed
toying with you...
all good things must come to an
end! [laughing]
[grunting]
[gasps]
Wait, are you?
Chibi‐Usa, accept the last
remaining bit of dream power I
have left.
[gasps]
Curse you, Helios! What won't
you do to mock me?!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[moans]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[grunts] Chibi‐Usa!
You're awake!
Sailor Moon...Helios!
Little girl. So you've broken my
curse, have you?
Well, no matter. You people are
still no match for me!
Have you all forgotten that I
possess the Golden Crystal?!
That's supposed to
be the Golden Crystal?
What?! [grunting]
Haha! Gotcha!
Take that!
Who's laughing now?
You little brats!
Here! Sailor Moon, catch!
[grunts]
Well what do you know, now
you've got the Golden Crystal!
With that, you should be able to
kick Nehalennia's butt!
Thank you.
Begone!
[screams]
Sailor Moon! Hurry!
Hmm.
[grunting]
[gasps]
Please, Golden Crystal, lend me
your power.
[gasps]
What happened?
[laughing]
Fools. You have no idea why the
Golden Crystal isn't working, do
you?
[grunts]
[whimpering]
It doesn't matter to the Golden
Crystal whether it's made to
shine...
by the power of my darkness, or
by the power of the beautiful
dreams of you humans.
(Queen Nehalennia) In other
words, it's a device that
accumulates any form of energy.
[gasps]
But the fact is, the people
living in your wretched world
are no longer capable...
of having dreams beautiful
enough to make that crystal
shine.
You lie! The people of Earth
have not yet lost their power to
dream!
Nonsense! The dim, lifeless
crystal she's got in her hands
is all the proof you need.
[screams]
[screams] Hmph.
Don't lose faith, Chibi‐Usa!
There are still many people out
there with the power to dream!
Hmph!
[gasps] Chibi‐Moon?
Everyone out there, can you hear
me?
I'm calling on everyone in the
world who possesses beautiful
dreams to please...
(Chibi‐Moon) ...please lend me
your power!
[sighs]
Right now our world is being
attacked by some very, very bad
people!
(Chibi‐Moon) These people are
trying to destroy our world!
[small gasps]
(Chibi‐Moon) If they get their
way, then our world, this
world..
where we're supposed to try
and make all our dreams come
true will be gone forever!
If we don't stop them, they'll
trample on our precious dreams
and destroy them.
And the people we love.
Please! I need you all to
pray with me right now!
I need you all to fight beside
me, by shouting out these words
with me!
Moon Crisis Power!
[sighs]
What? What is it, Unazuki?
Moon...Crisis...Power.
Huh?
Moon Crisis Power!
[gasps] What's happening?
[gasps]
It can't be! The Golden Crystal
is shinning?!
You see this? This is the light
of the beautiful dreams...
that Pegasus and all of
us have fought to protect!
The Golden Crystal only
unleashes its true power...
by answering to the beautiful
dreams of the people!
We'll show you the kind of power
that comes from having dreams!
The power of beautiful dreams!
Sailor Moon!
Right!
Moon Crisis Power!
[screaming]
(Usagi) Chibi‐Moon, what's
wrong? Wake up!
Come on, we still have so many
things we want to do!
We can't give up on our future!
We're going to grow up and
become adults together, right?
And make our dreams come true!
We can make them happen, I know
we can!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Dreams Forever: Fill the
Heavens with Light."
(Usagi) The moonlight is a
messenger of love.