(CHIBI‐USA) Hey, have you heard
about that big mansion?
(USAGI) You mean the one where
that weird, stingy old lady
lives?
(CHUBI‐USA) Yeah! But I guess
she's actually kind‐hearted and
a great cook!
(USAGI) Really? Some jerk must
be spreading nasty rumors about
her.
Hope they're ready to face the
consequences!
Or in the
name of the
Moon...
...we'll punish you!
(CHIBI‐USA) Potatoes...
Carrots... And... onions!
MEAT SECTION
That just leaves
the meat. What
should I get...?
We're having beef stew today.
(CHIBI‐USA) I want cream stew!
Are you serious?
We just ate
that the other
day!
Yeah, so what?
(MAYAKO)
I demand an explanation!
Huh?
I'm sorry, but
that item is
no longer on
sale.
I found that price
in an ad and walked a very long
way to claim it at this
establishment.
Raising the price because I
arrived a bit late is absurd!
Uh, please settle
down, ma'am. I'll
honor the sale price
for you.
Oh? Well in
that case, I'll
buy two.
Uh?!
[awkward gasps]
Wow...
(USAGI) The Secret Mansion: A
Menu of Love for You
Hm. It's started
raining.
Here you go.
What do you
think you're doing?
Huh?
Offering an umbrella
to a complete stranger...
You must be after something.
[gasp]
I won't fall
for your tricks,
young man.
[gasp]
W‐What... was that
about?
Ahhh!
Omph!
Mamoru...
He's lucky that
truck didn't kill
him.
What a rude
woman! Master
Mamoru was
just being nice!
Hmph! Well, I'm going
over there to give her a
piece of my mind!
Hey! Hold on!
Diana!
I've got you
now!
Woah!
Omph!
Oh my.
No! Diana!
(ARTEMIS) This is bad...
What if Diana
tries to speak
to that woman in
her human language...?
[gasps]
[meowing]
Just hold still...
See? That wasn't
so bad.
[shaking]
[chuckle]
[meowing]
Are you hungry,
kitty?
How would you
like to join
me for some
pot‐au‐feu?
[worried groans]
(DIANA) Wow... what a big
kitchen.
If I had known
I'd be hosting a
kitten today, I'd have
prepared some fish.
Mmm...
Thank you for
waiting.
Please, eat.
[meowing]
[lapping soup]
It's delicious! But...
Whose that bowl for?
I wonder if that means there's
someone else living here?
You know... it's been
quite some time since
I've had a guest here.
Smells good...
[gasp]
[grunt]
[sigh]
JUBAN SUPERMARKET
You walked under the same
umbrella with her? Mamo! How
could you, when you're dating
me?!
Hey, I was
only trying to
share it.
Yeah, but you
were sharing it
with another woman!
(MAMORU) Usako, she was older
than your mother.
Mamoru's weakness is that
he's always been way too kind
to the opposite sex.
Weakness? I think
it's a good
thing.
Well, in Mamoru's
case, it's kinda
both.
I wouldn't worry aboit it. Even
if he was interested in her.
that lady's way out of his
league.
Oh, so you
know her?
Of course! She's
infamous.
She's super wealthy and lives in
a mansion all by herself.
However...
However?
Well, she's known
to be really
paranoid.
She suspects anyone
who comes near her of being a
land shark trying to take
her mansion.
Wait! I think
we saw her
at the supermarket!
Mhm!
Oh how could you?!
You were just after that
lady's fortune, weren't you,
Mamo?
Now you're just
making stuff up.
Ignore her...
[gasp]
What is it,
Mako?
(MAKOTO) That man over there...
He's the executive chef
of a three‐star French
restaurant.
Even though he's Japanese, he's
regarded as one of the top five
French culinarians in the
world... Mr. Ono!
[gasps]
Nah, there's no way
a guy that famous would
be in a place like this.
[sighs]
Mako!
That was some
story.
(HAWK'S EYE) [sigh] Such a cute
middle‐aged lady.
Hm? Ugh!
She seems so
rigid.
When will you
two learn?
Older women have experienced the
bitter and sweet sides of life.
And they, much like dried
shiitake mushrooms...
...are more savory.
Is your taste
in women really
that skewed?
I'll never
understand.
[gulp]
[chuckle] Wait for me...
mademoiselle
Something fishy's going
on.
You seem troubled,
what's wrong?
A woman living alone
in a big house, preparing
meals for two people...
Doesn't that seem
weird to you?
Perhaps she's expecting
company.
Mm‐mm... Diana said
there was no
one else there.
It didn't seem like anyone else
live there with her, and yet
there were two sets of slippers,
cushions...
...and just about
everything else you
could think of
too!
So what? Like I
care about Mamo's
stupid umbrella mate!
[chewing]
I smell a crime
here. I'm almost
positive that house
is hiding a secret.
[chuckle]
Hey, why are
you laughing, Pegasus?
Oh... I'm sorry...
But... I still think it's more
likely that she's waiting for a
guest. It must be someone very
important to her.
Huh? Hm...
Pega‐‐ I mean... someone
said that I'm probably wrong,
but I'm still suspicious!
Maybe she's covering up
that her house is a hideout
for the bad guys!
I don't know about
that, but I do know she's
a good cook!
Huh?
It's that man Mako pointed out.
[sigh]
Oh! Uh...
Uh... Oh... Um...
[chuckle] Pardon me.
Hey, um... Are
you... a famous
chef?
Huh?
No. I'm just a foolish
traveler whose memories
of a past love brought him
back here...
...as embarrassing as
that is for
someone my age.
Age? But age
has nothing to
do with it.
Whether you're
in your 30's,
40's, or even
50's!
You can't change the
heart of someone in love.
That's what my Mommy and
Daddy used to say.
How inspiring.
Thank you, little
mademoiselle.
Oh wow. I'm
inspiring!
[sarcastic] Mm‐hm...
[grunt]
I think he
was thanking you.
May I help
you?
[gasp]
[meow]
Oh...
You're the kitty
from yesterday.
[awestruck]
So, your name
is Chibi‐Usa?
Oh, yes.
How did you end
up finding out that
Diana was visiting my
house?
Well, she insisted on coming
inside. And she usually only
does that when she knows there's
good food.
[muffled meow]
So, um... is there anyone else
living with you? I mean, since
this house is so big and all.
No, it's just me. I spent a
fortune to buy this big house,
but never invite anyone over.
It's them again!
Huh?
We're close.
So the woman Mamo
shared his umbrella with
lives around here, huh?
I think you're
over‐reacting.
I never overreact! This lady
might be attractive. And if she
is, you can bet I'll punish
Mamo!
Oh boy...
(LAND SHARK A) Hey! We know
you're home!
Huh? What's that?
Come on, lady!
We don't got
all day!
What's the matter
huh?
Quit giving us
a hard time!
Stop pretending you're
not home, would
ya?
Just get out here!
(MAYAKO) Go away!
Hmph!
This house will
never be for
sale!
[chuckle] Well, aren't you
just as stubborn as ever, lady?
Don't make this hard
on yourself, sweetheart.
It can be dangerous for old
people to live alone.
Who are you
calling old?! So
rude!
Those two thugs
are threatening
her.
Those two are land
sharks. Seems like the
rumors of them targeting
this house are true!
[angry growl] Huh?
Hey! Ow!
W‐who're you?
Just someone passing
by.
But, I couldn't
ignore a woman
in distress.
Ow!
Why you...!
Ah!
[grunts]
I'll make you
regret that!
Omph!
Ahhh!
[panicking] He's trouble! Let's
get out of here!
This ain't over,
ya pink haired
freak!
You're not hurt
or anything, are
you, madam?
What was that
for?
Huh?
People don't just randomly help
women they don't know. So you
must have some kind of ulterior
motive as well!
A motive? Well,
I...
And also, I have
no reason to trust that you
aren't teamed up with those
other men, now do I?
Anyway...
Thank you. Goodbye.
[growl] That woman made a fool
of me!
There's definitely something
going on here. Why does she act
so differently to people she
doesn't know?
(MAYAKO) It's because I want to
protect this house.
[gasp] Uh oh...
It's fine.
It's not like I
don't know what
rumors my neighbors
are spreading about me.
According to them, I'm
a weird, stingy old lady
who hoards all of her money.
No way! You're not stingy at
all! And you've been nothing but
kind to me and Diana since we
got here!
Thank you, Chibi‐Usa.
[shriek]
Ahhh!
My. What a lovely
home. Those men didn't look it,
but they certainly have good
taste.
No one gave
you permission to
be here!
What? You're not even going to
offere any tea? Well then, guess
I'll just have to get straight
to business.
[chuckle]
Ahhh!
One...
[gasp]
Two...
And three!
[pained cries]
Ah!
I was after
your dreams, not
your house.
Knock, knock. Coming
in.
Diana, I need
to go tell
the others!
[screaming] No!
[sigh]
Ugh. Pegasus isn't
here.
Well, no matter. Pegasus
or no Pegasus, I'll make her
pay for ignoring me.
[gasp]
Small Lady,
you have to
tranform!
[charging lunge]
[scream]
W‐What's going on?!
Hurry!
Hang in there!
[yelps and meows]
[panting]
Ah! Omph!
[groaning]
Usagi, hurry!
Huh?
Transform!
(USAGI and Chibi‐Usa)
Moon Crisis Makeup!
Enough! [grunt]
Ahhh! Omph!
Why you... that
was my face!
How dare you
scratch it!
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Hold it
right there!
How dare you apply
brute force to get into
this woman's home and
her heart!
That's breaking and
entering on two separate
accounts!
We're the
Pretty Guardians...
...who fight for
love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am
Sailor Chibi‐Moon!
In the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
You girls again.
How annoying.
Come forth my Lemures! Ms.
Autobiko, the Acrobatic Bike
Artist!
Ahhh!
Hi there!
Rules are for losers!
I ride how I want! I was
born to be wild!
Ahhh!
She's reckless!
This room is
too small!
On the ceiling!
[grunt]
On the wall!
Ahhh!
Anything is a
road if you
believe it is!
Ahhh!
[screams]
[chuckle] They're all yours!
[grunt]
Sailor Moon! Chibi Moon!
Would you take this fight
outside?! You're making a huge
mess!
But we're not making
the mess! She's the one
who's destroying everything!
[panting]
Ahhh!
[laughing]
[grunt]
Ahhh!
Look, it's Tuxedo Mask!
Sorry, I'm late.
Only a true
villain would destroy
a flower garden.
Curse you!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Chibi Moon!
Right!
Please Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
[straining]
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out!
(CHIBI‐USA) Gently, gently...
[groan]
(CHIBI‐USA) [gasp] You're awake!
[relieved gasps]
Who are you
two?
We're um... Chibi‐Usa's
baby sitters.
[gasp]
Uh...
The dreams that
he and I
shared...
What do you
mean?
(ICHIRO) Mayako...
Huh?
Ichiro...?
That's right. It
is I, Ichiro
Ono...
...the man who once shared
your dream to transform this
house into a restaurant 20
years ago...
Huh?! [gasps]
I'm leaving for
France to train!
Don't try to
stop me, Mayako.
Wait! What's going to
happen to this house we bought
for the resturaunt we dreamed
of?
I want to perfect the world's
finest flavors! I can't open a
resturaunt in a place like this!
Ichiro!
In those 20 years, I was able to
train hard enough to secure my
place among the world's top
culinarians.
But I never
found a pot‐au‐feu
that comes close to
surpassing yours.
I've always kept
a warm bowl
of pot‐au‐feu in case
you returned.
Mayako... Can you please
find it in your heart to forgive
this selfish man?
Of course. We
made a vow...
To do this
together.
(CHIBI‐USA) Not too long after
the two reunited... the mansion
was transformed into an amazing
restaurant.
(DIANA) Like they say, all's
well that ends well!
(USAGI) Our powers aren't
working! What are we going to
do?!
(PEGASUS) If you put your trust
in me, your true powers will
awaken. Please believe in me.
(USAGI) But Pegasus... How do we
know that you're actually on our
side? Can we really trust you?
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Believe in Pegasus: The Four
Guardians' Super
Transformation."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.