(Usagi) Okay, here's the story.
Turns out girls nowadays have to
go out and search for their own
Prince Charming.
But that also means that the
days of being a helpless damsel
in distress are over.
So you better think twice before
messing with my friends! Or
else...
In the name of the Moon, I'll
punish you!
Sailor Moon...
SuperS!
Sailor Moon SuperS
(Pegasus) The forest is
weeping...Our Crystal Forest is
weeping...
Are you there?...If you can hear
my voice, please answer me.
I've come running from the far
side of night just to find
you...And only you.
(Usagi) "Meeting of Destiny: The
Night Pegasus Dances"
[groan]
Someone's calling...They're
calling out to me...But who is
it?
[gasp]
[deep breathing]
(Chibi‐Usa) Uh...Hey‐ where'd
you go?...It was you, right? It
was you calling out to me.
(Pegasus)Tell no one...Our
meeting must be a secret.
(Chibi‐Usa) Uh?
Hey!...Why aren't you up yet?
[dazed]
Oh, well...It was just a dream‐‐
Okay, move! C'mon, everybody's
already there.
Hey! Put your arms up!
[groan]
(Makoto) So,...you're not
working today, Motoki?
Who'd be coming to the arcade?
Everyone's here.
Oh, yeah! I guess that's true.
Yeah, no one's gonna wanna miss
something that happens only once
every couple a'million years!
(Ami) Well, more like once every
few hundred years...You see,...
...the sun, moon and Earth will
be in alignment, with the moon
between us and the sun.
So for a few moments today, the
sun will be completely hidden
behind the moon. And that's
called a total eclipse.
Right!
All of a sudden, the sky goes
dark and the world gets
spooky...
Weird and terrible things begin
to happen...
The dead rise from their graves
and werewolves search for human
blood... [chuckle]
Knock it off.
Stop trying to scare her with
that bogus nonsense.
It's okay. Don't worry. Half the
time I don't even listen to her
bogus nonsense.
Whatta you mean? It's not bogus,
it's totally tru‐‐...Huh?
Wait, I'm thinking of the full
moon!
(Rei) Huh? Are you serious,
Usagi?! I don't think you're
thinking at all!
(Usagi) Come on. It was a simple
mistake...Full moon...No moon.
Chibi‐Usa.
Huh?
What's got you so spaced out?
Hm?
(Unazuki) I bet it's a boy,
isn't it? Did you have a
"Fateful encounter"?
Ooh!
Careful. Don't go doing anything
your mom and dad wouldn't
approve of.
Huh?
Oh, look who's talking.
What do you mean?
What's been keeping you at work
so darn late? Mom's beginning to
worry.
Whaa‐‐?! I don't know what
you're talking about!
Oooh...!
Hey, guys, it's about to start.
...Wow!...Whoa!
(Usagi) So this is how dark the
night would be without any
lights.
(Usagi) That's weird...Is that a
circus tent? I don't remember
that being there before.
(Rei) Hey, c'mon, Usagi! What
are you doing? We're leaving
without you!
Wait, I'm coming, I'm coming!
[laughing]
No one even noticed! Will you
look at that, no one even
noticed!
By the way, did I mention that
no one even noticed?
These humans are dogs and don't
even know it.
And they're raising their
children to be monkeys; they
don't even know that, either.
This whole place is nothing but
dogs and monkeys...
[cackling]
A circus tent suddenly
appears...
...Right, smack, in the middle
of their city...
...And, still, no one even bats
an eye. Hmm, why is that?
Yeah, why?
Why?
Why is that?
They're creatures who don't care
what happens beyond the walls of
their own little rooms.
And that's why...
...Even if giant rats chewed a
hole right through their
planet...
...Or, even if a giant circus
tent appears out of nowhere...
...No one in this city will ever
even notice!
[whooping]
(Zirconia) All right, quiet
down!...Quiet!
All right, hold on‐‐ Hold on‐‐
Ah! [popping] ...There we go.
Now,...
...the time has come at last for
us to establish our dominion
over this world.
Amazon Trio, are you present?
Tiger's Eye, present.
Fish's eye, present.
Hawk's eye present.
You summoned us, Madame
Zirconia?
I did.
Why?...Because I am quite
certain that the one we've been
seeking fled to this world.
Capturing him is the first step
to world domination, so,
obviously, he must be found.
(Zirconia) That is your task.
And you will begin by searching
for those humans possessing
particularly beautiful dreams.
Huh?
Um...Beautiful what? Did you say
"dreams", madam?
That's right.
You see, unlike you, the one we
seek is unable to maintain his
physical form for very long in
this world.
His existence is unsustainable
in the confines of the real
world and he would quickly lose
energy and die.
(Zirconia) However, there is one
way, and only one, that would
allow him to remain in this
world.
What's that?
It's this.
He could survive indefinetely by
hiding in someone's beautiful
dream.
Now I get it.
So what you're saying is that
we'll find him hiding in the
beautiful dreams of one of the
humans living on this world.
(Zirconia) Obviously that's what
I'm saying because that's what I
just said!
Now, there are many humans,
almost as many as there are
stars...
That being said, there can only
be a handful of them who are
capable of dreaming truly
beautiful dreams.
So, the one we seek can surely
be found...Now go out and find
him!
(Hawk's Eye) Hey. How 'bout this
one?
(Tiger's Eye) No, not my type
(Hawk's Eye) [sigh] It's not
easy. Even limiting our search
to the handful who have
beautiful dreams,
there are still so many...
Look at all these cuties. It's
just so hard to choose.
Yeah, well, this isn't about
your personal taste. The job
comes first.
None of them seem that special
to me.
Seriously, Tiger's Eye, you find
these girls appealing?
Well, we're not all as uber
particular as you are, Fish's
Eye.
Oh, this one's super‐cute. Wow,
I'll go with her.
Oh, glad you're keeping your
personal taste out of it.
I don't know, she's got that
wholesome look. That type is
really hard to get.
Oh, yes. I know. But even they
can be gotten if you make it
seem like fate threw you
together.
[chuckle]
There you go.
Okay. So what's the dirt?
What do you mean?
What's the story with you and
this boyfriend that your brother
was talking about?
Oh!
(Unazuki) Hey. Not in front of a
kid.
Ohhh. It's at a point where you
can't talk about it in front of
a kid, huh?
(Unazuki) Usagi, cut it out!
Hey, is this your boyfriend's
picture in this pendant?
Eahh! Let go of that! [grunting]
Chibi‐Usa! Stop that!
Oww...
Anyway,...
...he isn't my boyfriend.
Hm?
There weere a couple of times
when it got really close, but he
still hasn't asked me out, not
officially.
So, I gues, maybe we just
weren't meant to be...
You know, a girl doesn't
just have to sit around waiting
for a boy to make the move.
Hm?
Sometimes you just have to hop
on your white horse and go out
there and find Prince Charming
yourself.
After that, whether you have a
fateful encounter or not is up
to you.
Wow, Chibi‐Usa...
That was intense.
Hey. You've been peeking at
Mom's women's magazines again,
haven't you?
Wait‐‐ Where's my wallet?
(Tiger's Eye) Might this be what
you're looking for?
[gasp]
(Unazuki) Thank you so, so much.
Not at all. I almost got the
feeling we were meant to meet.
Perhaps it's fate.
Huh?
Seems a shame...to just say
goodbye and let it go at that.
Uh...
(Usagi) Chibi‐Usa...What's this
all about? Why did you drag me
way out here, this late at
night?
Usagi...
What?
Isn't there a forest with a
great big lake somewhere, right
around here?
Huh?...A forest? There's nothing
like that anywhere near here.
I guess...I was wrong.
[scream]
Huh?
Forgive me for startling you, my
sweet.
[gasp] Who are you?!
[chuckle] Now, now...Relax,
don't be scared. I'm not a
weirdo.
What do you mean? You're a total
weirdo!
[gasp] It's Unazuki!
Who's the blond weirdo with her?
Chibi‐Usa! Let's transform!
[grunt]
One...
[gasp]
...Two...
...And three!
[scream]
(Tiger's Eye) [chuckle] That is
a Dream Mirror, my dear...It
will allow me to look into your
dreams.
(Usagi) Hold it right there!
Who's that?
We're the pretty Guardians...
...who fight for love and
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And now, in the name of the
Moon,...we'll punish you!
...We'll punish you!
Huh. I din't know there were
country bumpkins in the city.
Come forth, my Lemures.
(Tiger's Eye) Karakuriko, the
automaton!
Kara, Kara, Kara, Kara, Kara,
Kara‐
Oh!
Oh, boy. And you thought he was
a weirdo.
How rude. Karakuriko, get rid of
them.
Kuri, kuri, kuri!
Where'd she go?
[gasp]
[groaning]
Sailor Moon!...
[groan]
(Usgai) ...Oh, this is getting
weirder by the minute!
Hey, let her go!
You! What's the big idea?
Kuri!
(Usagi) [gulp] Sorry I asked...
[yelling]
Sailor Moon!
[chuckle] We'll see how long she
can keep that up.
[yelling] Help!
Kuri?!
Huh?
(Mamoru) I cannot forgive
someone who would spoil a lovely
night like this with such
boorish antics.
It's Tuxedo Mask!
Good God. Where did you find
that tacky playboy getup?
Silence! I'm your worst
nightmare.
I am the rose of justice that
slashes evil.
You're a fashion nightmare,
that's for sure.
[grunt]
[shout]
[grunting]
[groan]
Huh! Looks like I win.
[grunt,...snicker] Looks can be
deceiving.
What‐‐?
(Tiger's Eye) [chuckle] You see,
my whip has tied your shadow to
that tree.
I think you'll find you're
unable to move.
[grunting] He's right!
Oh no! Tuxedo Mask!
See ya! By the way, capes are so
over.
No! Leave her alone!
[grunting]
Now, let me have a peek. I wanna
see if the one I'm looking for
is hiding in your beautiful
dream.
[scream]
(Tiger's Eye) Oooh!...Oh
my!...Interesting!...That's
kinda kinky!
Ohh...Too bad.
It's a beautiful dream, but,
unfortunately, he's not in
it...What a pity.
(Tiger's Eye) Still, to make
sure he can't ever seek refuge
in there, I'm afraid I'll have
to eliminate you.
Sorry about that.
Karakuriko! Go on and get rid of
them, and I mean all of them!
Kuri, kuri, kuri!
[yell]
(Mamoru) [grunting] I've...got
to get free...!
[grunting]
Kuri, kuri, kuri...
[grunting,...yell]
(Chibi‐Usa) We're all going to
die!...Please, somebody, help
us!...Anyone!
[yells]
What now?
Wait, is that‐‐? Pegasus is
here!
Huh?
(Chibi‐Usa) Sailor Moon! You all
right?
They changed into Super Sailor
Moons! But how?!
Karakuriko! Eliminate the two of
them, quickly!
Kuri, kuri, kuri, kuri, kuri,
kuri, kuri!
[gasp] What's this?
(Usagi) What's happening? I feel
my whole body overflowing with a
mysterious power...
Let's do this!
Hm.
Kuri, kuri, kuri, kuri, kuri!
Karakuri!
[yelling]
[scream] Stage Out!
That's disappointing.
[thudding]
[gasping]
What is that creature?
It's so beautiful...
[gasps]
Where'd it go?
[gasp] When did we turn back to
normal?
She's all right. She just
fainted, that's all.
Thank goodness!
(Pegasus) Tell no one...Our
meeting must be a secret.
So it wasn't a dream after all.
Hang on. Do you know something
about what just happened?
Huh?...No...What would I know
about it?
Hm.
Sailor Moon SuperS
(Chibi‐Usa) I wonder how long
the red strings of fate are...
(Usagi) Huh? What brought that
up?
(Chibi‐Usa) What would you do if
you had to be separated from the
one you love in order to pursue
you own personal dream?
(Usagi) That couldn't happen to
me because my dream is to marry
the one I love, Mamo! We'll
never be separated!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Super Transformation Again:
Pegasus's Power!"
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.