The world I live in,
Elysion, used to be
supported by the beautiful
dreams of the
people of Earth...
But then, one day,
without warning...
they came.
They came from the
chaos and darkness
of the New Moon.
They called themselves
the Dead Moon.
Tell me, Pegasus. What can
we do to save your world
from the Dead Moon?
The enemy is after the
Golden Crystal.
If it falls into
their hands, then not
only Elysion,
but the Earth, too
will be transformed
into a world of darkness.
We must not let
that happen.
The Golden Crystal? So as
long we have that, we can
save Elysion, the Earth,
and even you, Pegasus?
Is that what you're saying?
"Chibi‐Usa's Little
Rhapsody of Love"
This Golden Crystal that
can save Elysion, what
does it look like?
What kind of powers
does it have, Pegasus?
Well it's...
Right... You can't tell
me, I get it.
I'm sorry. I promise
I'll tell you everything
when the time comes.
Pegasus...
I might be just a kid, but
if there's anything I can
do, just tell me, okay?
Because I really do
want to help you,
Pegasus.
♪♪♪
Pegasus? Do you remember
the first time we met?
You were standing
in that dark forest
looking so sad and lonely.
Ever since that day...
since that moment when I
first saw you in that forest,
felt like time has stood
still for me...
... as if I'm living
inside a never‐ending
dream.
Pegasus, do you
believe in destiny?
Do you believe in
destiny bringing
people together?
The reason I was born,
why I exist... ever
since meeting you...
I feel as though I've
found the answer to
all of those questions.
Thank you. When the time
comes, I'll tell you
everything. I promise.
I know you will.
'Cuz‐ Well, 'cuz I
trust you, Pegasus.
It happened again. I heard
Chibi‐Usa up in her room
last night talking to
someone and she sounded
really serious.
She said she was on the
phone with Momo.
But I'm pretty sure
she was lying to me.
Really? You think she was
talking to someone other
than Momo?
Yeah. I definitely
got that feeling.
That can only mean
one thing... clearly.
Well, well, our little
Chibi‐Usa.
What?? What's it mean?
[chuckling]
Isn't it obvious?
Usagi, you're so dense.
Huh? Huh? Why're you all
looking like you know
something I don't?
Obviously, she's‐‐
‐‐in love with
an older man.
Mako, I think that's
a bit of a stretch.
So, what's going on?
In love?!
Yeah, in love! Clearly,
Chibi‐Usa has a boyfriend,
Usagi!
A...
...boyfriend??
But if it's true, why on
earth would she want to keep
it a secret from Usagi?
[chuckling]
Ami, that's the way it is
with a first love.
Her first love.
That's so sweet.
Yeah. Especially when it's
with someone older.
[gurgling]
Yeah, you really need to
stop saying that.
Well anyway, we'll have
to subtly get the truth
out of her.
[chuckling]
And once we do, we'll
be standing by with our
years of experience
to offer her emotional
support.
[chuckling]
[awkward chuckling]
Chibi‐Usa has a boyfriend..?
Huh. So Chibi‐Usa's in
love with a boy. I wonder
what this kid looks like.
[lightly grunting]
So frustrating!
I have the body of Helios,
the protector of the Golden
Crystal, in my power... yet
I still do not possess the
all‐important Golden Crystal
itself!
Zirconia! Are you there?!
Yes! I'm right here! You
summoned me, your majesty,
my most beautiful ruler,
Queen Nehalennia?
Zirconia... the time has
finally come for us to
claim this planet...
The era of the Dead
Moon is about to begin.
Indeed. Queen Nehalennia,
you are the only one fit to
rule, not just this planet,
but the universe!
Really. Then why haven't
you found me the Golden
Crystal yet?
Uh‐ It's not for want of
trying, your majesty.
Zirconia...
In case you hadn't
realized it yet, I have
grown tired of waiting.
Horrifying. Simply
horrifying...
Such laziness is shocking
beyond belief!
[sleepily laughing]
Granny Zirconia looks like a
dried‐up squid.
Ugh. I never order the
squid, I hate squid.
Palla‐Palla thinks squids
are scary.
Don't say she looks like
squid, it's not fair!
...To the squid, I mean.
Wake the hell up!!
[groaning]
Honestly! Sleeping in until
noon in a time of crisis!
[grunting]
What you girls need
is discipline!
Oh. It's the dried‐up
squid herself.
Quiet! Do your job! Find
out if that target is
the host of Pegasus!
And do it quickly!
Her majesty Queen Nehalennia
has grown tired of waiting.
Here you go.
Thanks, Rei.
Why'd you want to see me?
Oh, well, no special reason,
really. Nothing all that
important.
We just wondered how you
been doing lately,
Chibi‐Usa, what's
new with you?
You mean since I saw you
guys yesterday?
[grunting]
You guys are weird.
Chibi‐Usa? Are you sure
there isn't anything
you'd like to tell us about?
Hm?
Like maybe..?
... Someone older?!
Huh?
Mako, why do you always
have to go there?!
'Cuz it's the ultimate
female fantasy!
What is it you're
trying to ask?
Has there been something on
your mind?
On my mind?
That's right!
Not really.
Oh.
Except...
What?
Well, just there's
really nothing much I
can do about it...
[lightly gasping]
Whoa, sounds like a
tough one.
Don't worry, we're
here to help!
I'll gladly teach you
how to win a man's heart
through his stomach!
Or how to write a touching
and passionate love letter.
You've got nothing
to be ashamed of.
Right! You should be proud
of it!
There's nothing at all
wrong with falling
head‐over‐heels in love
with someone older.
What's this obsession you
have with older men?!
'Cuz that's usually
the way it is!
Usual how?!
Usual as in usual
for most people.
What the heck is going on?
Welcome! What'll
you have?
I want the rainbow
one and the yellow one...
It's on us, so go crazy,
and have as much as you
want.
You know you're like
a little sister to
us, Chibi‐Usa,
so you don't ever
have to be shy.
Right, if there's
anything on your mind,
we're here for you.
What're you trying to say?
Uh‐‐
Well, say, like if there was
someone you couldn't stop
thinking about, for example.
Hm?
Is there a person
you think about?
What sort of person?
What sort of person? I'm
not sure "person" is the
right word...
There's more than one?
Careful. Two‐timing can be
tricky if you're not
experienced at it.
Huh?
Have we met
him before? This
person?
Yeah! He's all
white and silky!
All white..?
...and silky?
Uhh‐‐
What else? What's
his face like?
Uh, his face? It's
very, very long.
Did you say long?!
Uh‐‐
Hey Ami, it sounds to me
like this guy's a real
horse‐butt.
Horse butt? No, Minako. I
think you meant to say
he's a jacka‐
What?
No, I can't say it.
It's too vulgar.
What?? You mean he's too
vulgar to talk about?!
No! No! That's not
what I meant at all!
'Cuz he does sound‐‐
Good grief.
Um, Mamo...?
Hm?
This restaurant looks like
it's really expensive.
Go on, Princess, you can
order anything you want.
Really?
Of course.
This is awesome! I
feel so lucky to go
on a date with you
at a fancy place
like this!
[chuckling]
If there's one person who
can get the truth out of
Chibi‐Usa, it's Mamoru.
Yeah, but he has to be
careful A young girl's
heart is complicated.
Especially when you're
two‐timing a guy.
That Chibi‐Usa. All
the times I've been
on dates with Mamo
and not once have we
gone to an expensive
looking place like this!
You're right. It looks
very expensive.
Good evening... Are you
ladies ready to order?
(all)
We're good with
just water.
[gasping]
I'll have a glass of apple
juice. A small one.
This isn't working.
We're too far away
from them!
I can't hear a
word they're saying.
We've got to get closer.
Yeah, so I guess that's it
for now.
Still, I suppose sooner or
later a date with me won't
be that exciting.
Mamo, you know you'll
always be my favorite.
Why, thank you.
But if you were to find
someone special, Chibi‐Usa,
you'd introduce him
to me, right?
Well, actually,
there is someone.
Could it... be
a.. boyfriend?
Not exactly...It's
complicated.
It's complicated how?
Uh‐ Mamo...
What is it?
Do you get the feeling
someone's trying to
listen in on us?
Because I definitely
get the feeling that
someone's trying to
listen in on us.
Nothing to see here.
Uh, Miss..?
Maybe make that apple juice
to go.
Oh, boy, now we've done
it. She's really upset.
I don't blame her.
And Mamoru didn't
look happy either when
he ducked out of there.
I guess we might've gone a
little too far.
Those nosy girls... Trying
to pry into my secret...
Uh‐
[gasping]
What's the matter?
Look, Ami! Over there!
That guy Chibi‐Usa's
staring at!
Huh?! [gasping] He's
all in white! And
he has a long face!
[groaning]
What? Are you saying that
he's the one? That's her
boyfriend?!
Huh! Finally, I've got the
target in sight.
[gasping]
It's her again!
Is there something I can
help you with?
Well, yes, as a matter
of fact, there is.
Just hold it right
there while I take a
quick peek at your dreams!
Orb Shot!
[grunting]
It's a total blank!
Thanks, Granny Zirconia!
All your big talk and it was
just...another false lead!
Hold it right there!
Huh?
Who do you think you are to
meddle with my daughter's
love?
To meddle with an innocent
young girl's first love!
To meddle with her love for
a super attractive old man!
To meddle with her first
shot at two‐timing!
To meddle with the
biokinetics of love science!
Wait a minute!...Who are you
guys talking about?!
If you mean me, you've got
the totally wrong idea!
Anyway‐‐
In the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
Man, you guys are even
chattier than usual.
Come forth, Paku‐Paku Dude,
the Dream‐Eating Carp!
Come, come, come, come!...
Bwah, bwah, bwah, bwah!
Ahh!
Don't be coy, Dude. Go
gobble up that guy's ugly
Dream Mirror.
Gulp! Splash!
[gasping]
His Dream Mirror!
Swim! Swim! Swim! Swim!
Swim!...Dive!
He's gone!
[puzzled chatting]
[screaming]
Craaash!
Chibi Moon!
Somebody helllllpp!
Come! Come! Come! Come!
[screaming]
grunt)
Waaahh‐huh?
Where there's a girl
troubled by love, that is
where you'll find me!
It's Tuxedo Mask!
Chibi Moon! Do it!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out! Gulp!
I'm glad things
worked out.
Now you and long‐
faced man can be
together.
Huh?
Hold on a second. that's
the guy you're in love
with?
No offense, but he seems a
little too old for you,
doesn't he?
Come on, there's a big age
difference between you and
me, too, Mamo.
Yeah. But he could
be her grandpa.
You guys, you're all
wrong about this!
Obviously. Who cares
if your daughter is
dating someone older?
No, it's that she's
two‐timing!
I really don't think
it's a good idea to date
two guys at the same time.
[chatting]
Quiet!!!!!!!!!
Like I told you,
you've got it all wrong!
The boy on my
mind is...
Is who?!
...a secret.
[groaning]
[sighing]
But you know, Pegasus...
one day, I will be able to
properly introduce you
to everyone... won't I?
I can't wait to grow up!
Why do you want
to be an adult?
You have way more
money to spend!
Yeah?
There won't be any
homework!
Keep going.
And best of all, no more
curfews!
So we can stay
out late and uh‐‐
Yep!
Even...
Ooh! You wanna go that far?
Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS, "Dream to be an
Adult: The Amazoness'
Confusion." The moonlight is
a messenger of love.