(USAGI) A young swordswoman
trains with passion!
(CHIBI‐USA) She fights toward
her dreams!
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Ah, but
life is so complicated!
(CHIBI‐USA) Hey, old lady! Don't
you love your own child?!
(USAGI) How could you crush a
young girl's heart?
(CHIBI‐USA) You're a super mean
mom!
(USAGI) We are the Pretty
Guardians!
And in the
name of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
Let's see if your
skills are as good
as they say. Now, face
me!
The Tenka Itto‐ryu Miharu
Akiyama! Attack at will!
Such an insolent child!
[charging yell]
[grunt]
You're mine!
[grunts]
She's not bad
at all.
People are right
to call her a "master
swordsman."
She willingly accepts all
challengers as her training
partners.
(USAGI) It's like watching an
old samurai movie!
(MAKOTO) That bridge is where
she's been camping out.
(USAGI) Really?
(REI) Since setting up there
three days ago,
she's dueled nearly ten
self‐proclaimed masters and
managed to beat every single
one.
MASTER SWORDSMAN
WILL TAKE ON ALL
CHALLENGERS
MIHARU AKIYAMA,
TENKA ITTO‐RYU
Miharu!
(USAGI) Chibi‐Usa?
Listen! I wanna
become strong. Make
me your student!
Since I am still in training,
there's no way I can take on a
student until I become the top
swordsman in all of Japan.
Sorry.
[gasp]
I'll throw in
three meals and
a nap time!
(USAGI) Aiming for the Top: The
Pretty Swordswoman's Dilemma
What?!
Well, I couldn't
just let Miharu
live under that
bridge forever.
I mean,
what if it
rained?
She's all
by herself.
I get all
that...
but what does
it have to do
with my room
looking like
this?!
Mrs. Tsukino set up the
room this way so that I could
practice my techniue in‐doors.
However, if I am an
inconvenience to you,
Usagi, I will return to my
tent.
Oh! It's really
no trouble at
all!
If using my
room helps to
fulfill your dream,
then you're welcome
to use it to practice in
as much as you'd like,
Miharu.
I am grateful!
(MIHARU) Kiai!
Wow, how cool!
So awesome!
Unbelievable...
Thanks so much!
I'm a bit concerned that
I may be showing off.
Oh, no. If anything,
you're being very
helpful, Miharu.
It is the least I can do to
repay you after all of the
hospitality your family has
shown me.
Are you kidding? Having a
samurai here is totally cool!
Your dedication is
really inspiring. 'But I can't
help but wonder how your parents
feel about this.
There is no
need for you
to worry
about that.
My father died
of illness
five years
ago,
and my mother...
Don't be... so single‐minded.
My mother is...
Oh, right. The onions...
Isn't
Miharu
great,
Usagi?
Mm... Well,
yeah, I guess
so...
Hmmm...
Look at this
one.
Her sharp little
nose... that petit
mouth... So cute.
Strong girls are worth the
effort it takes to torment
them.
(FISH'S EYE) Wow, you're sick.
Think it'll be that easy? It's
unusual for one to dream of
becoming a top swordsman these
days.
She might not fall for your
usual charm, you know.
My, you're completely clueless,
aren't you, Hawk's Eye? Well,
it's no wonder your plans never
succeed.
Women are able to find hapiness
in different ways. They're not
all the same, you know.
Well then, Mr. Expert...
If you'e so great, perhaps you
can show us how it's done.
If you insist. [chuckle]
See you soon...
my sweet, little
Miharu.
Kiai!
Who's there?!
You're still here clinging to
your precious practice, I see.
[chuckle]
[charging yell]
Look, a
challenger!
Good luck, Miharu!
I know you can do
it!
You go this!
(USAGI) She doesn't stand a
chance against you!
[grunt]
[gasp]
Kiai!
[grunts]
[gasp]
[charging up]
Huh? Ah!
Oh no!
[chuckle] You
left yourself
wide open!
Ah!
And you think
you have what
it takes
to become the top
swordsman in
Japan?!
[chuckling]
Ah!
Quit it! You've
already won! Isn't
that enough?!
Stop it!
[groaning] Usagi,
stop... it's
okay...
This woman is
my mother..
[gasp]
Hmph! You can't even beat me,
and yet you still dream of
becoming the top swordsman in
Japan?
Don't make me laugh! Just give
it up already!
[laughing]
Why is she
like that?
(MIHARU) My mother doesn't
really like the idea of me
trying to become Japan's top
swordsman.
She always tells
me that I should
just give
up.
But it was also my father's
dying wish, so I cannot simply
do as she wishes and quit!
Why does my mother
not understand how
badly I want
this?
Hey, Miharu,
you're crying...
Hush!
Crying?
Mother, I can't
stop crying...
That's because you're
trying too hard when
cutting them.
[weepy breaths]
[sobbing]
Miharu...
I'm gonna go
have a talk
with her...
Anyone home?!
AKIYAMA DOJO
TENKA ITTO‐RYU
Anyone home?!
Uh?
[panting]
What are you
two doing?
Huh?
Oh, uh, sorry
to bother you,
ma'am...
Usagi, not
like that!
Wait, what? Oh,
you're right.
I think that Miharu has a lot of
potential, and if you really
love her, you should support her
ambitions to the fullest!
Yeah, what she said!
If you're her mother,
then maybe you
should practice
sparring with her,
or try to teach
her some new
techniques, or
something!
Anything that'll help her dream
along!
Keep your noses out of our
business.
This is between
me and my
daughter.
But you have to
understand that Miharu
really needs you right now!
Yeah! Don't you
know that she's
been out there
training with a
single‐minded
purpose?!
That's exactly her
problem. Miharu is
too single‐minded.
Huh?
Anyway!
I have nothing
more to say
to the two of you.
Wait, come back!
Why are you
so unreasonable?
Please just
think about...
...how all
this affects
Miharu!
You jerk! Even
Usagi is a
better person
then you are!
Um... I'm
not really
sure how
to take that?
Well, it's the truth.
Excuse me?!
[raspberry noise]
Why you...!
Why? Why can't I beat my
Mother? I want to be Japan's
best swordsman...but how?
[panting and heavy breathing]
Huh?
Who's there?
Spring has come and
gone. The birds cry a
parting song. The fish
are weeping.
Torazo Miyamoto of the Dead Moon
ryu.
Miharu Akiyama of
the Tenka Itto‐ryu.
Oh my, impatient, aren't we?
Would you join me for tea?
I am in training and do not
have time.
I see. Too bad. I do admire your
diligence.
But, if that's the case, shall
we begin?
One...
Huh?
Shoot...
Was it nothing?
Close one.
Oh, she is good.
Let's duel.
Kiai! Challenge accepted!
[charging up grunt]
What is that
technique?
[grunt]
Kiai!
It... vanished?
[chuckling] Looking for this?
When did he...?
Here I come!
Kiai!
[thrusting grunt]
[cocky chuckle]
I win!
That... can't be!
I dodged it... I
know I did!
How...?
MUSASHI MIYAMOTO
Now, right as
I'm about to
leave...
Please!
Wait just
a moment!
[giggling] Just
like in those
Japanese samurai
films!
Your sword technique is simply
incredible! So I take it that
you must be a very reputable
swordsman, sir.
N‐not at all...
[clears throat]
I am a
follower of...
Takezo Miyamoto's
sword style.
T‐Takezo Miyamoto?
Uh? How do you not know who
Takezo Miyamoto is? He was the
man who once dueled Kojiro
Sasaki on Ganryu Island.
Do you mean... Musashi
Miyamoto, then?
I‐It's read as
"Musashi"?
Well, someone could
have put a
note on how
to read it...
Um...
Yes. The one who's
name was left out of
our history books because
it was too similar.
Takezo Miyamoto.
The legendary swordsman!
And I use his unbeatable
sword style!
Please!
Allow me
to be your
student!
Finally, we're getting
somewhere.
Normally, I would never take on
a student. However...
You... I may be able to make a
special exception for. You can
thank your dreams. Come with me.
Y‐Yes!
That lady is just the worst! I
feel sorry for Miharu having to
deal with that meanie as a
mother! Right, Usagi?
That's her problem. Miharu is
too single‐minded.
(CHIBI‐USA) Hey, what's the
matter?
Miharu's mother
might not be such
a bad person after
all.
Really?
I guess I kinda
get the feeling she's
being mean to her on
purspose.
How so?
It is possible
she has a good
reason.
Yeah, like what?
How should I
know that? It's
not like I can
read her mind!
Listen... all I know is that no
mother could ever hate her own
child. There's no way...
Mhm.
(MIHARU) How far are we going?
True swordsmen must
train in the most
secluded area
possible.
So, do you
wanna go next
time?
Yeah, sure. Huh?
That's Miharu.
Oh, you're right.
Who's that weird guy she's with?
(MAKOTO) Wait a sec...
That's the way
to the cemetery..
Something doesn't feel
right.
This spot will
do.
My technique is
not something that
can be acquired
so easily.
I am well‐aware
of the risks
at hand.
Then close your
eyes until I
tell you to
open them.
Why?
You want to
become strong,
don't you? Or
do you doubt me?
(MIHARU) No, never!
That's a good
girl. Now, don't
move until I tell you
to do so. [chuckle]
(MIHARU) Such an evil aura...
What is this?
One...
Two...
[gasp]
[chuckle] I don't think I
remember telling you to open
your eyes.
Let me go! What... are you?!
Hmph. I guess you shouldn't
blindly follow strangers.
Your silly single‐minded desire
to become stronger, made you
oblivious to my trap.
Now... enough talking. Show me
your dreams.
And Three!
[screaming and losing
conciousness]
[panting]
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Moon
Crisis Makeup!
[pained screams]
[chuckling]
He's not here.
Oh darn. I put so
much effort into this
one, too.
Well, time to die!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Huh?
[annoyed grunt]
Not only did
you crush her
dreams...
But you have
also mocked the
spirit of the
sword!
The Sun might
overlook your evil
deeds...
...but we will
never forgive
you!
We're the Pretty Guardians....
...who fight for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
In the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
Come forth, my Lemures...
Ayatoriko the String Expert!
Does anyone want to play a game
of Cat's cradle with me?
I'm Ayatoriko!
(USAGI) Oh
man, it's
another
weirdo!
Ayatoriko.
Please clean this mess up. I'm
counting on you.
So which one of you wants to
play a game of cat's cradle with
me?
Check on Miharu,
Sailor Moon.
Don't worry, we
can handle this
creep.
Mhm!
Fire Soul!
The Tunnel!
Huh? [scream]
Miharu, are
you okay?
[groaning]
[gasp] Sailor Moon! Thank
you!
Curse you, monster!
Let's play cat's cradle! My
turn!
The Star!
(USAGI) Look out!
(SAILOR GUARDIANS) Woah!
(CHIBI‐USA) Eww!
What the heck is
this wet, gooey
stuff? Gross!
Miharu!
You have to
get out of
here!
No!
I would never let
myself do something
as cowardly as run away!
Bushido... is
about dying in
battle!
[charging]
(USAGI) Miharu! Please, stop!
The Broom!
[charging] Woah!
You see? You
should have
listened!
Supreme Thunder!
[hard grunt]
Let's play cat's cadle.
(AYATORIKO) One‐step ladder.
[dodging grunts]
(AYATORIKO) Two‐step ladder.
Three‐step ladder. Four‐step
ladder.
Five‐step ladder!
[screaming]
Play cat's cradle
with me!
[annoyed grunt]
Just leave this
one to me. Hey,
Ayatoriko!
Are you going to play cat's
cradle with me?
From what I've seen, you can do
up to a five‐step ladder... But
can you do six?!
Huh?!
[frustrated] Ayatori!
Ayatori...! Ayatori...
Ayatori... [defeated sigh]
Now!
Burning Mandala!
Ayatori!
Look out!
[grunts and groans]
Miharu! Get out
of here!
[struggling]
Curse you!
The Rubber!
MIharu!
(MAKOTO) Drop your sword!
Run!
A samurai cannot abandon her
sword!
Why don't you come play cat's
cradle with me?
(REI) This is no time to be
stubborn!
(CHIBI‐USA) Miharu!
Don't be...!
...so single‐minded!
You have to run away now!
[gasp]
Aya aya aya...
Now is your
chance!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyon'e dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Ayaya.. Stage Out!
We did it!
Nice job, Miharu!
Thank you, everyone. It was
really quite interesting to
fight in such a chaotic manner.
[awkward giggles]
But now I finally understand.
Everything.
See, if you heat
the knife first, onions
won't make you cry.
Wow! That's amazing,
mother!
(FUYUMI) Hmph. You must be
feeling quite confident if you
called me out here today.
Let's begin!
[grunt]
Prepare yourself!
Kiai! Umph!
Yes, I won!
[grunt] What's this about?
You were right,
Mother.
I was so intent on becoming a
strong swordsman, that I
completely lost sight of
everything else.
From here on out, I will expand
my horizons and one day become
Japan's top multi‐talented
swordsman.
So you finally understand.
I do!
However!
I cannot condone
using such cowardly
tactics in battle!
[giggling]
You are in
big trouble!
[giggling] Sorry! But
I never stated we had
to use our swords.
Alright, quit while
you're ahead, kido!
[sigh]
Those two are
something else.
Usagi, do you
think that MIharu
will ever accomplish
her dream?
Of course, she will!
Especially since she
has her mother's full
support!
[chuckle]
(USAGI) Oh, Rei! [chuckle]
(REI) What? You're creeping me
out!
(USAGI) Guess what?! A popular
designer asked me to be his
model!
(REI) Seriously?! Why would he
pick you over me and my amazing
figure?
(USAGI) And I'm going to have
him make my wedding dress!
(REI) An animal costume would
suit you better...
(USAGI) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS: "We Love Fashion: The
Stylish Guardians."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.