(USAGI) Pointe shoes... A white
tutu... Everything I need to
become the lead in a ballet!
(CHIBI‐USA) If you're gonna look
silly no matter what...
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Then dance
like no one is watching.
(CHIBI‐USA) You'll still be bad!
(USAGI) Whatever! I may lack
talent, but with my youth and
beauty...
The lead role
of Giselle...
Will be mine!
(CHIBI‐USA) So pretty!
(USAGI) Ballet is definitely
"in" these days.
YAMAGISHI BALLET COMPANY
PRESENTS: GISELLE
(USAGI) It says here...
YAMAGISHI BALLET COMPANY
"Seeking new dancers for
'Giselle'. No experience
necessary. Offering free lessons
for beginners."
Then that means...
Mm‐hm!
The two of
us...
Actually have a
chance...
Of being in
the show!
WITH ME AS THE LEAD OF COURSE!
Alright!
Let's do it!
(USAGI) Become a Prima: Usagi's
Ballet
(REI) You joined a
ballet company?
Really, Usagi?!
[chuckle] I'm going to
be in "Giselle."
Isn't that the story
about the girl who dies
of a broken heart after
her lover betrays her?
And then later she
becomes a fairy and
convinces the other faries
to spare his life, right?
So, did you
get cast as
Giselle in it?
Of course not! Although...
they did say the role that
I got was practically
tailor‐made for me.
(MINAKO) And you, Chibi‐Usa?
Mm‐mm... They said
that was too
young.
Well, congrats, Usagi.
But it seems so odd.
Why would you, Usagi,
appear in a romantic story
like "Giselle"?
A good judge of
talent can tell when
someone like me has
hidden potential!
A good judge
of talent...
Put you in
the show?
Uhhh...
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
YAMAGASHI BALLET COMPANY
Hurry up, Usagi!
Hold on...
I just have
to put my
shoes on.
[gasp]
No way...!
So cruel...
How could they?!
Is it because they're
jealous of me getting
a big role? But I have worked
so hard...
I won't give up!
I will overcome these obstacles
and become Japan's... no, the
world's top prima donna!
Did you put that tack there so
you could copy the scene from
last night's "Star of Ballet"
episode?
[nervous chuckle]
Does it... Go
like this?
Or maybe this?
How do I
look?
Usagi, it looks
like you've put
on a little
weight.
Huh? No way!
Stop! What're you doing!
Wah! I'm so sorry!
(KYOSUKE) Come on. Kiriko.
Huh?
I've told you
before; Giselle is
a fairy.
So if you can't
suppress your humanity
then this performance is a
failure.
Now, I want
you to do
that part over
again.
Yes, sir.
Woah...
But I think
she's really good...
So even someone
like her has
trouble...
[chuckle] Well, I have
always wanted to
wear a leotard.
The lead role
is sure to
be mine.
Alright, let's start the
beginner's class. Kiriko, we'll
work on that part again later,
so stick around.
Yes, sir.
You two, please
step forward.
Yes, sir!
I want you both
to meet the newest
members of our class.
Okay, come in, everyone.
(SAILOR GUARDIANS) Yes sir!
Huh?!
(CHIBI‐USA) You guys?
(USAGI) But why?
We thought it'd
be more fair
if you had
some competition.
So we decided
to take the
class too.
Plus, moderate exercise
is really good
for the mind.
It'll be fun.
Yay! I'm so
excited!
The lead role
is mine!
[chuckle]
Oh, hey. This
girl's new to
the class too.
How do you
do?
A pleasure to meet you!
Likewise.
Oh boy, they
seem annoying.
Let's get started
now. Get to
the barre.
First position, the
plie.
[strains and groans]
Extend.
And back. And
plie.
[strains and groans]
Straighten your back,
please.
[groaning] Woah!
Sorry...
Legs up on the barre.
Slide and stretch.
Sorry!
A la seconde.
Knees straight.
Yes, sir!
Omph!
Ah! Sorry...
Im fine, really...
[pained sigh]
Huh?
Wow...!
Amazing...
So pretty...
Wow, she's good.
Incredible!
But somehow... She
seems cold.
Almost like she's not of this
world.
(KYOSUKE) Giselle...
You!
Yes?
Can you stay
after class today?
Huh? You want
me?
Yes.
I think watching
you will expand
my image of
Giselle.
If it means I
can help, I'm
more then happy
to stay.
Thank you so
much.
Mr. Yamagishi! Wait! You're
going to give her the role of
Giselle, aren't you?
[gasp]
Just hold on.
Please, let me
explain myself.
I don't want
to hear it!
That's enough! It was clearly my
fate to be betrayed by the
person I trusted the most, just
like Giselle was!
Kiriko!
[sigh]
Sucks for her. The lead
role is mine. Along with Mr.
Yamagishi's heart, of course.
[chuckle]
[heavy sigh]
[deep breath] Let's continue.
[whining] I'm tired.
Usagi, hurry up
or we're going
to leave you
behind.
How about we
go to Crown?
Sounds good! We're
going on ahead!
Huh? Wait up!
I'll wait for
you, but hurry
up.
(STUDENT 1) So then that new
girl is Giselle?
(STUDENT 2) Yeah, That's right.
Huh?
(STUDENT 1) What'll happen to
Kiriko?
(STUDENT 2) Who knows.
(STUDENT 1) Come to think of it,
she and Mr. Yamagishi are always
arguing.
Usagi, this way!
Hey look!
Huh?
Isn't that the
girl from class?
Looking back, I
think I may
have overreacted.
I'm sure most people
would be upset if their
teacher took away a lead
role from them on a whim.
I know we constantly argue, but
Mr. Yamagishi wouldn't do
something like that without a
good reason.
And now I
know...
I realize that I'm
just not good enough
to be a lead dancer.
I'm so ashamed.
No way. You're
amazing!
[gasp]
It's a little hard
to describe, but
your ballet just seems
so warm and gentle to me.
I never imagined watching
someone dance could make me
feel happy.
Thanks so much.
When it comes to
ballet, Mr. Yamagishi
gets into a zone where
nothing else matters.
Woah.
His passion for
it is absolutely
incredible.
I get it!
You have a
crush on
Mr. Yamagishi!
[gasp and chuckle]
Giselle becomes a fairy
after the man she loves ends
up betraying her...
...but she still tries
to help him despite
all of that, because she
truly loves him.
I thought that maybe I could be
like Giselle. I really want to
help Mr. Yamagishi, even if he
doesn't return my feelings.
But...
Then you should
just try to
do your best
for him.
You think so?
Yeah! If you
do that then
something good is
sure to happen.
Well, when you say
it like that, it really makes
me feel like it might work.
She's right. Let's
all try our
best.
Though Usagi's best
still isn't good
enough.
Mm‐hm!
Hey! Was that
really necessary?
[chuckle]
You're both right. I'll
just do my best and keep
on moving forward.
Chibi‐Usa and I
know you can
do it.
Thank You.
I can tell how
much Kiriko loves
ballet dancing and
Mr. Yamagishi...
But why can't
he see that?
He may not understand
her feelings right now, but
surely he will someday.
Oh. You think?
There are times
when people pursuing
the same path
face difficult challenges...
...but their bond
helps them eventually
come to an
understanding.
[sigh] Wow. Being a
grownup sounds hard...
(Pegasus)
I bet Mr. Yamagishi is thinking
about Kiriko
Yeah... I just hope
things work out.
♪ Sailor Moon
[exhale] I think
that's enough for today.
Thanks for the lesson!
Of course!
We're making good progress, so
I'd like us to start doing stage
rehearsals a bit earlier than
planned.
Sure!
Great, thank you.
Hm. Hey, Mr. Yamagishi are
you thinking about Kiriko?
No. I was thinking that I should
probably apologize for putting
you on the spot before.
Oh, that didn't bother me.
But& I feel bad for Kiriko.
You know, Mr. Yamagishi,
it seems like you don't
know much about women.
has eyes for her.
Know what I mean?
What...?
I want you to see only me and
show me your beautiful dreams.
...will you do that? Please?
[gasps]
Huh?
Uh good evening! Silly ol' me
forgot my ballet shoes here.
I mean, it's not like we were
trying to spy on you or
anything.
That's right. We
were just watching you
two from the shadows.
Dummy! Hush!
Well, uh, Guess we'll
be on our way ...
Really? What bad timing!
It's getting late, so please be
safe on your way home, girls.
‐Right! Goodnight, sir!
Oh, Ms. Tsukino...
Yes?
Could you also come to the
theater tomorrow? I want to
rehearse that role I mentioned
before.
Sure!
(Thinking)
Score! My first step towards
a prima! I can't wait!
I'm here and even though I
couldn't be Giselle, I still
want to help his vision of her&
in any way that I can.
Thanks for coming. I really
appreciate it.
Of course. I'm just glad I
could be of help to you.
Because of you, I can finally
perfect Kiriko's Giselle.
'Kiriko's Giselle'?
This whole time I
thought you chose me.
Huh?
I truly apologize for not
explaining things to you
thoroughly,
but I've never considered anyone
other than Kiriko for Giselle.
So then you basically tricked
me for your own benefit!
I feel so
used!
I'm sorry. I did have a major
role lined up for you.
Stop it!
If I'm not playing the
lead, then what's the
point of even being here?!
Besides, I'm way better
than she'll ever be!
While I agree that you have
better technique than she does,
by letting Kiriko play Giselle,
I believe the experience will
help her develop into an amazing
ballerina.
That's right& rather than
playing her as a perfect fairy
An imperfect Giselle, who has
room to grow, is sure to capture
people's hearts.
She doesn't have
to be so detached.
Excuse me?! What are
you talking about?
As long as Giselle's pretty,
what does it even matter?!
The way Giselle looks isn't
nearly as important as her
ability to appeal to people's
emotions.
I want to be able to touch
people's hearts through ballet.
,,,That's my dream.
Do you really mean all that?
Kiriko...
I'm so sorry I never realized
that this was how you felt
this whole time.
I've been struggling with how
to put it into words,
but now I know how to bring out
a performance that suits you,
Kiriko.
Mr. Yamagishi!
[happy tears]
I cannot believe you're just
completely ignoring that I'm
here!
That's it! [snap]
[gasps]
I was supposed to be the
one deceiving people here,
but you made me look
like a complete fool!
[attack yell]
Kiriko!
(Fish's Eye)
You're all washed up!
One...
Two...
And three...
[screaming]
(Usagi & Chibi‐Usa)
Moon Crisis Make‐Up!
♪
Let's have a look,
then, shall we?
[screaming]
Not here either!
No Pegasus means that
you have to die then.
(Sailor Moon)
Hold it right there!
You doused his
flames of passion!
How dare you do that to a
man who has devoted his
whole life to art!
We are the Pretty Guardians&
We fight for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi‐Moon!
And in the name of the
Moon we'll punish you!
Ugh! I'm not in the mood to
deal with you today. Get lost!
Come forth, my Lemures,
Kurumiwario, the Nutcracker
doll!
I am Kurumiwario,
the Nutcracker doll!
Oh great, it's another weirdo!
an't somebody else deal
with it this time?
Hey, I can hear you two!
I'm leaving the rest
to you, Kurumiwario.
Right. I will turn them into
fine prima ballerinas.
Well, just do what you can.
'kay, bye!
Now then, becoming a top
prima ballerina means hard‐work
over talent! Understand?
Huh?
I will demonstrate my
technique for you.
Legs like this...
So, what now?
Let's beat him up
and be done with it.
Pay attention, you two!(
‐Right!
ow! Grand Fouette . An Tourne!
Tourne tourne tourne...!
This is my secret technique!
7, 8, 9, 10, 11&
Ooo...
So awesome!
30, 31, and 32!
So, how did you like that, huh?
That was great!
So talented!
All right, girls, now
it's your turn to try.
Huhhh...!?
Together we will...!
Together we will...?
Aim to become...!
Aim to become...?
The& Star of& Ballet!
[attack yell]
[screaming]
Ahhh....! Wait...
that was it?
So cute!
Hey, you! The tall one!
You're too big!
You're bursting out of it!
Nobody asked you!
It does look tight...
Don't poke me!
A true prima ballerina has
to maintain her figure.
I'll spin you twice
as much! Begin!
What's happening?!
[shouting]
Spin 'round and around!
Ahhhh stop it!
I think I'm gonna throw up&
Me too...
If that made you dizzy, then you
haven't practiced enough!
You call this practice!?
Now that you're warmed up, shall
we move on to the exercise?
What!?
There's still more?
No one said becoming a prima
ballerina would be easy! Coming
up next...
Grand Battement !
[scream]
Is that his brain?
It's a walnut!
(Sailor Moon)
My least favorite nut!
Would you quit slacking off?
We're not slacking
off at all!
Raise your legs higher! Begin!
[shouting]
Keep your chins up!
‐Ahhh!
‐Stop it!
[screaming]
Keep trying and you'll get it.
It seems as though I have
nothing left to teach you two.
Really?
Does that mean we're done?
Now you can dance in hell!
[yelling]
What gives you the right to
crush these girl's beautiful
aspirations?
I, Tuxedo Mask, will
never forgive you.
Your name's "Torpedo Ass?"
I said, "Tuxedo Mask"!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
[neigh]
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out!
[groans]
Kiriko! Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, Tuxedo Mask!
I need a hug, too!
Sailor Moon...
Yeah...?
You might want to consider
working out a little more.
Huh!?
You got lucky this time, but...
What?! Just how long do
you watch us before you
come to help us out?
You can't be a Sailor Guardian
if you always rely on others.
What was that?!
You need to learn to take
better care of yourself!
I don't wanna hear
that from you!
♪ classical music
The two of them dance
so well together.
I thought Usagi
was in this?
Oh yeah. I haven't
seen her yet.
Does anyone know what
kind of role she got?
Uh, she actually told me not to
tell you guys, but...
[whispering]
(All)
Huh!?
This is what he meant by "the
perfect role for me"?
It's not fair!
(Usagi)
So I guess I'm going to be queen
in the future, aren't I, Mamo?
(Mamoru)
Yeah, and I'm supposed
to be the king.
(Usagi)
Then that means this could be
our last chance of having any
free time.
(Mamoru)
Just think of all the boring
royal events we'll have to go
to.
(Usagi & Mamoru)
[sigh] I'm beginning to
feel a bit feverish&
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS,
"Juban Holiday: The Carefree
Princess."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.