[eerie music]
Is this true, my beloved queen?
It is... The Dream Mirror of
Pegasus's host will not look
like anyone else's.
It will shine golden because of
the Golden Crystal.
Do I make myself clear,
Zirconia?
Look for the Golden Mirror.
Find and capture the one who
possesses the Dream Mirror that
shines like gold.
It will be done.
There are very few beautiful
dreamers left who could
potentially be his host.
So I assure you, Pegasus will
be in our hands very soon.
Use those four girls wisely.
But be careful to never
let your guard down.
Yes, your majesty... lovely
Nehalennia, the True Queen
of the Moon!
♪
(Usagi)
"The Amazoness: Nightmare from
Behind the Mirrors"
‐Ooooh!
There. Perfect.
Wow!
(Momo)
Hey Chibi‐Usa, did
you hear about Aki?
I sure did.
She's so lucky. She got
to go see it with her
mom last week, right?
Yeah. And of course she
said it was totally amazing.
[groan]
What is it? What's going on?
It's about this!
(Mamoru)
Huh?...The Dead Moon Circus?
(Motoki)
It's that big circus tent
they put up downtown.
They asked us to put up ads for
it here in the Juban Shopping
District.
Oh...
Oh, Mamo? I have a
question for you.
Can you guess where your
favorite cute and adorable
little Chibi‐Usa wants to go
more than anywhere else?
It starts with a "c"
and ends with an "s."
[grunt]
No way.
Why not?
Mamo, if you're taking someone
to the circus, it should be me,
and only me.
Nobody has the right to come
between two people who are in
love.
Wait, are you two
dating or something?
Yup! In fact, we're planning
to get married someday.
Uh, Usako? I think you're
wrinkling my shirt.
Humph!
Awww!
Isn't it nice that your
big sister has such a
wonderful boyfriend?
When you grow up, Momo, I'm sure
you'll find a man who's just as
crazy about you.
Crazy?
Really? So all I have to do is
wait till I grow up and I'll
have a wonderful boyfriend of my
own?
Ohh, I can't wait to be a
grownup, then. It sounds fun!
Huh?
[happy giggling]
I don't think I've seen
those girls before.
[gunfire]
Yeah! Vaporized him!
[beeping]
Girls, we need to go...
We're being summoned.
By the way, I think
you've got it wrong.
About what!?
Being a grownup is dumb.
They always have to get
permission to do anything,
even just to dream.
Yeah, take it from me, becoming
an adult is nothing that any
sane kid would look forward to.
In other words, refusing to grow
up and remaining a child forever
is really your best option.
Always remember not to forget.
A child's dream is a dream they
should never get....
...Always remember not to
forget. A child's dream is a
dream they should never get...
...Always remember not to
forget. A child's dream is a
dream they should never get.
Huh???
Whoa, kids these days sure
are cynical, aren't they?
Not having a boyfriends who're
crazy about them must've
warped their personality.
Will you please stop?
A child's dream is a dream
they should never get. Always
remember not to forget...
...A child's dream is a dream
they should never get. Always
remember not to forget...
...A child's dream is a dream
they should never get. Always
remember not to forget...
...A child's dream is a dream
they should never get. Always
remember not to forget.
Eureka! I've figured it out!
I've figured it out! I've
figured it out!
Ah! It seems the young boy has
finally managed to figure it
out!
He finally figured out that the
only time he's allowed to dream
is when he's sleeping.
And then‐‐!
‐‐in the blink of an eye‐‐!
‐‐that was the moment the young
boy grew up and became an adult.
[squawk]
That's when you find out
your beloved prince...
‐...is really a toad in the
mirror.
The magic of dreams can make him
look like a prince, but his
voice is that of a toad.
But can't you make your dreams
real‐‐
‐‐even when you're‐‐
‐‐an adult?
That's asking for
the impossible.
That's a dream that will
never ever come true.
So enjoy the fruit
while it's still ripe!
Eat it up while
innocence remains!
Always remember not to forget.
A child's dream is a dream they
should never get!
...Always remember not to
forget. A child's dream is a
dream they should never get...
...Always remember not to
forget. A child's dream is a
dream they should never get...
...Always remember not to
forget. A child's dream is a
dream they should never get...
Always remember not to forget.
A child's dream is a dream they
should never get...
...Always remember not to
forget. A child's dream is a
dream they should never get‐‐
(Zirconia)
Silence!...I said, silence!!
Humph!
Cere‐Cere, the Flower Master.
Palla‐Palla, the Ball Balancer.
Jun‐Jun, the Acrobat.
And Ves‐Ves, the Beast Tamer.
We're the Amazoness Quartet!
Yes and you're also very late!
Where have you been
all this time?
Frankly, you're lucky we came
at all, Granny Zirconia.
...we may not look it, but we're
extremely busy right now.
So if you've got something to
tell us, get on with it, okay?
Yeah, and quick! 'Cuz
Palla‐Palla's in a hurry and
wants to go back to playing her
game.
(Zirconia)
Quiet, you fools!!
[gasps]
I didn't awaken you just so you
could play and come and go at
your convenience!
What sort of progress have you
made in your search for
Pegasus's host?
We haven't even
started looking!
The truth is, we don't have to
take orders from you, Granny.
Yeah, Palla‐Palla doesn't
like being bossed around.
You can't possibly be serious.
And what if we are?
Then you leave me no choice!
If my words aren't enough
to make you obey..!
...Then, what?
Yeah, you gonna fight us?
Sounds like fun. Then I can take
over this circus from you!
Orb Attack! Hiya!
[grunt]
[charging up grunt]
See ya, Granny!
Hiya!
[screaming]
[grunt]
Y' kinda blew it, didn't ya?
Palla‐Palla got a big owwie.
Oh, please, you're not going
to cry about it, are you?
They're strong. If all four
had attacked at once, I would
have been in real trouble...
[concentrated grunt]
So, learned your lesson?
Dealing with you is as easy as
taking candy from a baby...
Now, enough of this nonsense!
Go and find the one in whose
dreams Pegasus is hiding!
Huh?
That's the girl from the arcade!
So... who's going?
I think the one who got her
butt kicked should have to go.
Ah, right.
Fine, if that's the way you want
to be, okay, no problem. I'll
go.
[car horn honking]
Ah! Hi, girls!
Huh?
You again!
Yeah. Sorry about all that.
All what?
You know, those things my
friends and I said at the
arcade...
We didn't mean to
offend you. Really.
What do you want?
Just to give you these.
Really?! You're gonna
give us two of your
tickets to the circus?
No, you can have all of them.
Huh? Thanks, but,
we can't accept them.
Of course you can!
C'mon, don't worry about it,
I've got plenty more.
This way you can bring
all your friends.
Hope to see you there!
(Thinking)
Always remember not to forget.
A child's dream is a dream
they should never get.
♪ Sailor Moon
[carnival music]
Whoahh... I've never been
to a circus before.
Are the tents this big so that
all the elephants will fit?
I've been to lots of circuses
and this circus seems bigger
and better in every way!
I'm super
excited!
Mhm!
Calm down... You're acting like
a couple of five‐year olds!
Let's not forget. We're only
here to help chaperone
Chibi‐Usa and Momo.
‐Yeah, we're counting on you!
Don't you worry. We'll be right
by your side the entire time!
Yup, so you can sit back
and enjoy the circus.
Oh, there she is!
Okay. Now all we have to do is
get her away from her friends.
Leave that part to me, I'll
figure something out.
[crowd cheering]
[circus music]
[gasps]
[giggling]
[crowd cheering]
Huh??
[awe]
[giggling]
[crowd cheering]
Huh? What's wrong?
Hey‐‐ Momo! Where're you going?
|
The show, it's not over!
Momo...
Usagi! Something's wrong!
[giggling]
Wait‐‐... What just
happened? How did I‐‐?
[giggling]
Thank you so much for coming.
Look, there she is! Momo‐‐!
Hold on! I think we should
Transform first...
Good Idea...
[giggling]
Who‐‐ Who are you?
Now, let's have a look at that
Dream Mirror of yours, shall we?
Orb Shot!
Ahh!
Huh?...That sure isn't
a Golden Mirror.
So disappointing.
Granny Zirconia. The old witch
gave us a bum lead!
(Sailor Moon)
Hold it right there!
This was meant to be a
fun night at the circus!
And you're going to
pay for ruining it!
We're the Sailor Guardians...
...who fight for
love and justice!
In the name of the Moon...
we'll punish you!
Aha. So you're those Sailor
Guardians Granny told us about.
I'm delighted to make
your acquaintance
Seriously? Palla‐Palla's not
delighted at all!
It's called sarcasm, dear.
It was nice of you to drop
in, but don't interfere.
My wild beasts are hungry
and it's feeding time.
What kind of wild beasts?
Come forth, my Lemures!
Gara‐Gara Girl, the
Dream‐Eating Serpent!
Gara‐Gara Gara‐Gara Gara‐Gara!
Gara‐Gara Girl!
[hissing]
Think she's hungry for
a dream mirror?
Gara‐Gara Girl, eat it while
it's nice and ripe!
[attack roar]
She took Momo's Dream Mirror!
[gulp]
Thanks for the meal, it was
delicious!
How could you!?
Chibi Moon!
[attack roar]
[attack grunts]
What should we do? If we attack
now, we risk hurting Chibi Moon!
Huh. What are they so
upset about? It's only
a Dream Mirror.
And a useless one at that.
The girl should be thanking
us for disposing of it.
Momo's dreams aren't
useless! Give 'em back!
[grunt]
Ahh!
No!
You'll pay for that!...
Fire Soul!
Ow! Hot! Hot! I'm a living
being, so I can't stand heat!
Now's our chance.
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
[neigh]
Check it out!
That's Pegasus?
[neigh]
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out!
Party's over...
They're gone!
[gasp]
Hey. We better return
Momo's Dream Mirror to
her, don'tcha think?
Mhm!
(Masseurs)
Rub down, rub down, Push and
press, Prod and poke, Lose that
stress.
Rub down, rub down, Push and
press, Prod and poke, Lose that
stress....
Ah, this is heaven!
Yeah, right there,
that's the spot.
[groan] Looks like we may be
stuck with this lame
Pegasus‐finding job for awhile.
Hope not... It's too much work.
Palla‐Palla likes to play
a lot more than work.
Well, if nobody else wants to
do it... then I guess I'll just
have to step up and volunteer to
go after the next target.
No, no. I feel bad making
you do all the work, Ves‐Ves.
I'll do the next one.
That's all right, you girls
relax. I'll do it.
Oh yeah, Funny how all of a
sudden everyone wants to do it.
[dreamy sigh] Did anybody else
think that Pegasus was really,
really pretty?
Totally.
And we're supposed to just hand
him over to Granny Zirconia...
Seems like such a waste.
I suspect that sooner or later
those girls will come to the
conclusion that they should keep
Pegasus and his power
for themselves.
I don't trust them.
I fear that if we don't do
something, they will eventually
become a threat.
Leave them be.
Let them go about their
business as they see fit.
Your job is to keep an
eye on them, that's all.
But, my queen, I‐‐
Are you questioning my orders?
Me? No. Never, your majesty.
I will do just as
you say, of course.
That's right. You will do
whatever I tell you to do and
you will do it without
hesitation...
...after all, I am the
forever‐beautiful Nehalennia,
the True Queen of the Moon.
[evil chuckle]
♪
(Ami
I heard the most
wonderful melody...
I feel like something inside
of me is about to change...!
(Usagi)
What do you mean, Ami?
(Ami)
I can't describe it, it's like
something tickling my heart
or is it tingling...?
(Usagi)
Wait, could it be..??
(Ami)
What?
(Usagi)
Ami! Are you falling in love?!
(Ami)
No! That's not it!
(Usagi)
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"True Power Explodes: Ami's
Melody of the Heart."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.