(USAGI) How dare you attack
famous fashion designer, Yoshiki
Usui!
(CHIBI‐USA) Yeah! His cute
designs are a gift to this
world!
(USAGI) That's right! Plus, he's
supposed to make a special
wedding dress just for me!
(CHIBI‐USA) What?! That's not
fair at all!
(USAGI) Not now! We have to
fight!
In the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
[chattering]
YOSHIKI USUI
Yoshiki Usui...
His stuff's
great!
Who is he,
anyway?
(REI) He's a popular
up‐and‐coming fashion designer.
(USAGI) That outfit's so cute!
I heard that he's opening up a
store in the area soon.
(CHIBI‐USA) So he's doing this
fashion show to celebrate, huh?
(REI) He said that his goal is
to continue expressing young
women's dreams through his
outfit designs.
(USAGI) That's so cool!
(MAKOTO) Young women's dreams,
huh?
(USAGI) We Love Fashion: The
Stylish Guardians
[chattering]
Look! There he
is!
Oh my gosh,
you're right!
So, that's him?
Who else could
it be?
[cheering and screaming]
Not only are
his designs cute...
..so is he.
Amazing...
He's the real
deal.
Wow! Look there!
Ahhh...
Now that's a
wedding dress...
[cheers and applause]
[sigh]
(FISH'S EYE) [humming]
[giggling]
Yoo hoo... So, how do I look?
I'm wearing a Yoshiki Usui
original.
I saw his show today, and I
just had to buy it. [giggle]
And this one?
Not really my
type.
Don't ignore me!
Disgusting. There's another
guy in here.
It would make my life so much
easier if someone would just
make a law against men having
beautiful dreams.
No way! It's
him!
Ugh!
(FISH'S EYE) This is Yoshiki
Usui! He's so cute!
[squeal] I can't
believe how lucky
I am! [giggle]
Cross dressing again?
No, not this time. I was
planning on going out to meet
him just as my beautiful self.
[giggle]
What are you doing?
Oh, today
I went to a
fashion show
with everyone.
And the last outfit they
presented was a wedding dress.
It was so beautiful!
I wonder who will stand next to
you when it's your time to wear
a wedding dress.
Stand next to me?
I mean the one who will take you
as his bride.
How did I not think of that? If
I want to wear a dress, I guess
I should have someone to marry
first.
Don't worry. You
still have plenty
of time ahead
of you.
Do you think...
that I'll find
someone special?
Yes. I know
you will.
You're still at it? Try not to
work so hard. You don't want to
get sick, do you? Besides,
what's the rush?
The fall winter
collection is‐‐
Yes, I know!
Hm?
[sigh] I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to yell.
[sigh] So this is
what it's like
to being in
a slump...
Ah... That feels
nice...
Since the start of my career,
I've designed so many outfits
using young women's dreams as a
theme.
Maybe I just need something new.
Something different...
[gasp]
Oh!
Excuse me!
Yes?
[gasp]
[chuckle]
Beautiful... This is
it.
After all this time
searching, you're just the
person that I need to fill me
with insperation.
How would you like to become my
exclusive model?
[chuckle] I'm a guy.
I don't care
about that! To
me, your beauty
transends gender.
No one else I've
seen captures that
pure ideal of a young
woman like you do.
Do you really
think I can do
it? [chuckle]
[chuckle]
Please, stop moving.
We can't measure
you properly.
How can I
stop, it
tickles!
[giggling]
Ow!
[gasp] Sorry, it's because
you moved.
Oh, so you're
saying that it's
my fault?
No, that's not
what I meant!
Well, then be
more‐‐ Ah!
Ow!
What is wrong with you?!
(STAFF B) I am so sorry!
(FISH'S EYE) You suck at this!
Jeez! You don't
have to be
so mean, you
know!
She's right! You're
being rude!
Hmph! Fine, then
I guess I'll
just leave.
Please don't. We deeply
apologize.
Usui needs your help.
Won't you please stay
and finish this for him?
[snickering]
[annoyed grunt]
[gasps]
Fine, then change this into
something more to my liking.
And then I'll agree to help you
out.
Uh... But, that's not my
call...
Got a minute?
I just finished drafting a few
new designs. Wanna take a look?
Sure.
[gasp] Show me!
Hm... What do you
think?
Hmmm...
Still needs work.
[chuckle] May I?
[gasp]
See? If we
change this, and
put that there...
Hey! Cut it out!
[grunt]
Ah!
How rude! I
thought you wanted
my help!
We wanna create outfits designed
by Usui, not by you. I suggest
you stop interferring with our
work.
Hey. Fire this
guy.
Huh?
Well, what are
you waiting for?!
Wait a sec! He's
been acting as my
assistant since I first
started out as a designer.
And you really think I care?
It's either him or me.
Are you serious?
I don't think it's
right for you to quit
just because you don't
like something.
Who asked you?
So which is it?
You're being a bit
harsh. Why don't we
just drop the subject,
okay?
Uh‐uh!
[sigh]
I'll make this
easier for you.
Huh?!
Keep letting your
brand flourish. Good
luck out there.
[sigh] I'm sorry...
(FISH'S EYE) [chuckling]
[laughing]
(USAGI) [gasp] Look! I saw this
one in the fashion show the
other day!
It's so cute!
Oh! I like this one, too! [gasp]
But wait, look at this one!...
She's been like this for an
hour. Ummm... Do you think you
could somehow convince her to
quiet down a bit?
Well, I'll try...
The Usui brand
is the best!
Don't you agree,
Mamo?
Usako... why don't I
buy you something so
we can be on our way?
[giggling] That's okay. Just
being able to look is good
enough for me. Oh wow, it's so
adorable!
No, please. I insist.
[gasp]
Mamo... Do you
really love me
that much?
Sure. Let's hurry
and get out
of here.
Why hurry? It's
only been six
hours...
EMPTY
Thanks Mamo! You're
the best!
Um...
If you could guess
three words to decribe
how I feel, what would they
be?
Um... "My boyfriend's
broke?"
No, silly!
I'm so darn happy! [chuckle]
[chuckle]
And by the way,
I'm pretty sure
that was four
words...
(FISH'S EYE) These are
fantastic! Much better then what
you had before.
Thank you. I
owe all of
this to you.
I want you
to stay by my
side forever.
[chuckle] Well, of
course. It's not
like you could do any
of this without me anyway.
We've decided that we no longer
wish to work here.
Hey wait a
minute! But, why?
Don't worry about them. Who
needs people who don't have good
fashion sense when you have
someone like me?
I'd like to
be alone now.
Moody artists are
so unappealing.
(YOSHIKI) [grunting] Why?
Why don't they seem to
understand?
Can't they see how hard I'm
trying?
[swinging grunts]
Ahhh!
(YOSHIKI) Damn it!
(USAGI) Mr. Usui?
[grunt] Huh?
Wow, it really
is you, Mr. Usui!
What luck!
And you are...?
Oh, right. I'm
Usagi Tsukino!
[giggle]
I saw your fashion
show the other day.
My favorite part was that
beautiful wedding dress.
Right after I saw it, I made a
promise to myself! I'm going to
wear one just like it when I get
married.
Yeah? I'm so
glad. Hm?
So, Mr. Usui...
I have a small request
if you're willing to hear it?
Okay?
I didn't want to ask because I
might come off as shameless, but
then I realized that I am
shameless!
Uh? Alright, well
what's your request
then?
Since you asked... I
wanted to have you design
the dress for my future wedding.
For free.
Ah! You think
I'm shameless now,
don't you?!
Oh! Well, maybe
just a little.
[weepy breaths] I was
hoping you wouldn't
agree with me! [crying]
[deep breath]
That's okay. I
didn't think you'd
actually do it.
[laughing]
[laughing] I'm so sorry
for laughing.
Usagi, right?
That's... my design,
isn't it?
Yeah, it is!
My boyfriend,
Mamo, bought it
for me.
(YOSHIKI) Is Mamo the one you'll
be wearing the wedding dress
for?
He sure
is! [giggle]
Do you like
my designs, Usagi?
Of course!
Why do you?
Uh...You... wanna
know why?
They're cute, and
stylish... hmmm...and,
uh... they're uh...
They're what?
Well, they're uh...
hmmm...
I don't know!
I guess I
just like them,
that's all.
You "just like
them', huh?
Is something wrong,
Mr. Usui?
I guess you
could say that.
Are you in
a slump?
[gasp]
[sigh]
You know... at a
time like this, designing
a wedding dress for me might
actually do you some good.
[laughing]
Uh?
You really are
shameless, aren't
you?
[awkward chuckle]
Now I actually
want to design
a wedding dress
for you.
[gasp]
You mean it?!
Yes, I do.
[gasp] "I want to design" ?
That's right... I'd forgotten
this feeling for so long.
What?
How did I let this happen?!
I've just been mindlessly
working! And because of that, I
let myself lose sight of loving
what I do!
It's not wonder
my designs were
garbage.
Uh?
Thank you!
Because of you, I
was able to find my
passion for designing
again!
Yeah?
As thanks, I'd like
to extend the offer
to design your wedding
dress.
I have no idea
what's going on,
but I accept!
Feel free to
visit me at my
studio anytime.
Okay!
Just goes to show, it never
hurts to ask.
Especially when there's
nothing to lose.
Ah!
What was that
for?!
There's no way
Yoshiki Usui would
design a wedding
dress for you.
Then why don't you go ask him if
you think I'm lying! He said
that I could visit his studio
whenever...
...so let's go now and I'll
prove it to you!
Huh? His studio?
Can we really
go?
Of course we
can!
So cool!
What do you
think of me
now?
Hmmm?
[laughing]
Ah!
(CHIBI‐USA) That's for bragging!
(USAGI) Then I guess you're not
coming!
(CHIBI‐USA) Wait, I'm sorry!
(YOSHIKI) Hideous!
I can't believe I designed
these!
They're just animal
costumes!
What're you doing?
I'm re‐doing my
designs.
How could you?
Sorry. I don't
need you to
model for me
anymore.
Fine.
Well, then I guess
it's time to end this
game.
What the...?!
One...
[gasp]
Two...
Ah!
And three!
[screaming]
That's Mr. Usui!
Mhm!
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Moon
Crisis Makeup!
[groaning]
Where is Pegasus?
[gasp]
[scoff] Well, this was just a
waste of my time. No need to
keep you around.
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Hold it
right there!
Stylish outfits bring
happiness to those
who wear them!
It's unforgivable that
you'd bully someone
who makes them
for us!
We're the Pretty Guardians...
...who fight for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
In the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
Hmm...
What is it?
Say... when you're out there
jumping and flittering about in
those short skirts, do either of
you feel embarassed at all?
Huh?
Hey, have you?
Uh... Not... really...
Me neither.
We haven't!
I see. How
silly of me
for asking.
Come fourth, my Lemures!
Gomumario, the Sea Lion Ball
Act!
Gomumario, make
sure you get rid
of these stupid,
shameless girls.
Wow, he's good!
Well, I can't say
I was expecting
this one...
It's time to pay
you back for what you did to my
second cousin, Pooko, the
Balloon Lady!
Ahhh!
Time to die!
I'll leave the
rest to you.
Ah! Please don't
eat me!
[menacing laugh]
[screaming]
[laugh slowly fading]
Uh... I guess
I caught him...
Okay, not bad
at all!
[struggling]
Ah!
Oh!
But it won't
happen again!
[lunging grunt]
[screaming]
Ahhh!
Oh!
Ah!
Kiai!
Ahhh! Ahhh!
Omph!
[groaning]
[laughing]
Flat as a
pancake!
[laughing]
Looking beautiful in the
latest fashion is the ultimate
wish for all women all around
the world.
And I'm here to protect all of
those pure wishes!
Tuxedo Mask, you made it!
[scoff] What a show
off!
[straining]
What the..?!
Ew, so gross!
[laughing] Here I come!
[charge up] Kiai!
[screaming]
Nice pass, Sailor
Moon!
What?!
Chibi Moon!
Right!
Please Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out, man!
[moaning]
Thank goodness. You're
awake.
Sailor... Moon..?
[gasp]
[chattering]
YOSHIKI USUI FALL/WINTER
COLLECTION
[chattering]
But why
are they
all miniskirts?
They're so
cute!
Look at that
one.
Huh?
[chuckles]
(MINAKO) Doesn't it look a bit
Sailor Moon‐ish?
(SAILOR GUARDIANS) Sure
does. Yup.
Oh my gosh! Do you think that
one could be my wedding dress?
[gasp]
Excuse me?
Don't think
we didn't
hear that.
Oh! Uh, you
see, it's kind
of a long story...
[nervous laugh]
(REI) This should be good.
(MINAKO) Spill it!
(AMI) You shouldn't keep secrets
from friends.
(USAGI) Well, I, uh...
(SAILOR GUARDIANS) Well, what?
Mr. Usui, please continue to
share your dreams with the
world.
(USAGI) Wait a minute... What do
you mena you have two
boyfriends, Minako?!
(MINAKO) Just call me, Ms.
Popular! What's a girl to do
with two handsome men fawning
over her? [haughty laugh]
(USAGI) Sounds like you sold
your soul to the devil. Your
parents would be so ashamed!
(MINAKO) Farewell, my dark days
of youth... And hello to a
future of happiness!
(USAGI) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS: "Storm of Love: Minako's
Grand Two‐Timing Plan."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.