(USAGI TSUKINO) What? Mamo is
cheating on me?! You're lying!
(CHIBI‐USA) Look Usagi...
There's no telling how Mamo
would react if he ever meets a
woman who's way more mature and
prettier than you'll ever be!
(USAGI TSUKINO) Huh?! No one
better try to break me and Mamo
up because if they do then...
In the name
of the Moon...
... we'll punish you!
The Perfect Couple: Usagi and
Mamoru's Love
(KOBAYASHI) Hey, Saori. Have
you ever been to Chiba's place
before?
(SAORI) No, never.
I'm willing to bet
a guy like him keeps
his place pretty messy. What do
you think?
How should I
know? What makes
you think it
would be messy?
Because real men
aren't big on
tidying up. That's
why!
Well, then, I
guess your place
is spotless, huh,
Kobayashi.
Ooh, ouch!
So, do you
think he's gonna
invite his girlfriend
over?
May we come in?
Hey! Thanks for coming, guys!
Come on in!
(SAORI) It's really clean.
Yeah, I'm actually
a little disappointed
in him.
What're you two talking about?
Oh! Uh, it's
nothing! [nervous
chuckle]
If you say so...
By the way, is your report
done Saori?
Yep, I turned it in a while ago.
Yeah? I should
have known.
Hm? Kobayashi?
Uh?!
Something bugging you?
Kinda, I noticed you don't
keep any photos.
Photos? Of what?
Seriously?! I'm asking you why
you don't keep pictures of your
girlfriend around!
[chuckle] Now that you mention
it, I guess I don't.
You've never noticed
before?!
Whoa, chill out!
Does it really
matter?
Of course it does!
Did you even invite your
girlfriend over to meet us
today?
Uh, she should
be here any
minute now.
Huh!
Speak of the
devil. Excuse me.
Can you, please,
stop pestering him
about his girlfriend?
Hey, I'm only
doing this for
you Saori!
What the heck
do you mean
you're doing this
"for me"?
[chuckle] Don't play coy.
I know you wear a different
color lipstick on days you
meet with him.
[gasp]
[chuckle] I'm right, aren't I?
You know I could kick your ass,
right Kobayashi?
Uh‐huh, hey‐hey... I
was only trying
t‐
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Mamo,
where are you? I missed you!
Huh? What the...?
[nervous laugh]
Hey, would you two please let go
of me?
I don't wanna!
If anyone has
to let go,
it's you, Usagi!
Why me?
Because he's my
Mamo, that's why!
What do you
mean he's yours?!
I'm his girlfriend!
Hey! That's my spot
you're sitting in! You
better get off of him right
now!
(CHICI‐USA) I'm not moving!
(USAGI) See if I bring you next
time!
I always come
by myself anyway!
You're so annoying!
Hello! I'm so
sorry you had
to witness all
of that just now.
Good afternoon.
I'd like you to meet
Saori and Kobayashi.
They're friends from college.
This is Usagi Tsukino and this
is Chibi‐Usa. I hope you can all
be friends.
[laugh]
Nice to meet you. Hello!
So, that means your girlfriend
is...
Yes. I am Mamo's, I mean,
Mamoru's girlfr‐
I'm Mamoru's
real girlfriend.
I think that's
just about enough
out of you!
Why don't you
just leave already?
[uncontrolable laughing]
[growling]
(MAMORU) Usako!
[chuckle]
This is all your fault!
Aww, just cut
it out!
'Kay...
I'm sorry. Your
girlfriends are just
too cute. Here,
have some.
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Yay!
Girlfriends... I get it now.
If you don't
mind me asking...
[chewing] Why yes, I
would love to
have another piece
of cake.
I was gonna
ask your age.
[nervous chuckle]
Oh, I'm 15 years old.
15, huh?
Yeah!
What a great
age.
You think so?
You have so
much to look
forward to.
Yeah, I guess I still have a
lot to experience. Well, at
least my love life is settled
with Mamo!
[happily eating]
[laughing]
Miss Saori!
Oh, yes?
So what is your relationship
with Mamo, anyway?
[gasps]
Well... Mamoru and I
have actually been classmates
since we were in high school.
Hmmm...
[nervous laugh]
You know, even back then, your
grades were always a lot better
than mine were.
(SAORI) Oh, please...
Bet you'd never guess it, but
she plans on becoming a police
officer after she graduates.
Wow! A police officer?
She wants to
be Japan's first
female Police Superintendent
General!
Don't make fun!
I wasn't! I
swear. I thinks
it's really admirable.
Superintendent General? So
cool. Go on and
break that glass
ceiling. Mhm!
I feel like Mamo knows her a
little too well to be "just"
classmates...
(FISH'S EYE) She looks like the
perfect honor student type.
You know... a straight arrow
who's always picked as the class
representative at school.
I know exactly
the type.
Overachievers who study too
much, prepare things ahead of
time, and follow the rules
down to ever detail.
The teacher's pet.
The type that tells
on you for making
even the smallest mistakes.
But... they are
inexperienced when it
comes to love.
So what you're saying is, this
girl happens to be exactly your
type.
It's just part of the job.
[kiss]
(USAGI) Look at this! Aw,
they're so cute!
I wanna buy both of them! Oooh!
But, I only have enough
allowence to get one... Hmmm....
I can't decide.
Which one of them
do you like
better, Chibi‐Usa?
Usagi, don't you
ever feel worried?
What do you
mean by that?
Have you ever stopped to think,
"Is this really how I wanna live
the rest of my life?" or "Will I
ever find true happiness?"
Or do you just not care?
What makes you say that?
Of course I worry about things.
Like, right now, I'm worrying
about whether I should get the
hippo or the horse.
I can't decide which one of them
is going to make me happier!
Hey!
And by the way Usagi, those
things are dog toys.
What?!
Well, then, uh... Maybe I'm
thinking about getting a dog,
okay!
Well, then, don't forget to buy
it some earplugs so it doesn't
have to listen to you.
Just who does she think she is,
anyway?
CURRENT TEMPERATURE
[chuckle] Well if it isn't my
cute little honor student.
Excusez‐moi.
Uh?
Huh?
Eh, what time is it now?
Oh, um... It's
about 5:30.
Oh! Is it
really that late
already?! Woe is
moi! [sobbing]
Is everything okay?
[sobbing] My guide say to me
today, please meet me at this
place at five.
I cannot get to
restaurant if my guide is
not here to help me!
What is your name?
Uh...
You are warm and with a pretty
face. it is most beautiful.
S'il vous plaît, I would love it
if you join me for dinner
mon chéri!
That's very kind of
you, but I'm actually
waiting for someone.
I'm sorry!
Oh mon Dieu!
[sobbing]
Hey.
Oh, Mamoru!
Huh?
Sorry for being
late.
Not at all.
Bye!
[grunting]
[snickering]
What are you
two idiots laughing
at?
Were you trying
to be charming?
Well, if you ask
me, you came off
as more of a creep.
Shut up! [sigh] It seems like
I'll just have to force her to
be mine.
[snickering]
I want you to break up with me,
Usako.
[gasp] Mamo?
The truth is, Saori
is the one I love. I've
finally realized it.
Why?!
We were made for each other!
Can't you see that?
No... No! No!
Please forgive me.
Mamo, come back!
Give my regards
to Chibi‐Usa.
But if we do not get married,
Chibi‐Usa won't exist anymore!
Ahhh!
This is bad... It might be the
biggest problem I've ever faced.
I've gotta fix this!
[panting]
[stumbling]
[gasp] Is that...?
No way!
Hm...
[surprised yelps]
[nervous laugh] Oh, hey...
M‐Mister... Kobayashi...
I'm sorry. You
weren't busy were
you?
Nope.
Just let me
know if I'm
bothering you.
It's fine, really.
Don't worry about
it.
[relieved exhale]
So what exactly did you need me
to help you shop for?
[embaressed breath]
Is it for a guy you like?
[gasp]
At our college, those two are
known as the school's best
couple because they look so good
together.
They're so perfect for each
other.
[sigh]
I really wish Chiba had an
actual girlfriend...
That way I still might have had
a chance with her.
Don't give up!
Huh?
I'll be rooting for you, okay?
[panting]
Fight! Fight! Kobayashi! Go for
it! Go for it! Kobayashi!
Kids are so innocent... [sigh]
Hmm... Hmm...
This one! Hmm...
No, this one! Hmm...
Hey!
[scream]
Chibi‐Usa! What
was that for?
Put the toys down! If you keep
this up, you're going to end up
losing Mamo for sure!
Huh?! To who?
To Saori, of
course! Are you
that oblivious?!
The two of you are as
different as chalk and cheese,
and you're definitely the
cheese.
If you really think that
Mamo's love won't fade, you're
in for a rude awakening.
Saori has way more going for her
than you do! She's prettier,
more mature, sexier, and
smarter!
Actually, I bet she'd make a
great mommy.
But, as much as I hate to admit
it... I can't be born unless you
and Mamo end up being together!
So, are you
starting to worry
now?
Mamo... I don't
want him to
hate me! [crying]
You finally get it.
Now, can you please
start acting more mature...
Kidding! [laughing]
I think you're the one
who doesn't get it, Chibi‐Usa.
I'd never doubt Mamo's love for
me.
Now, let's focus on more
important things. Should I
go with the hippo or the horse?
Ow!
Is it someone
I know?
Huh?
The guy you're
giving that tie
to as a
present.
You're curious today,
aren't you?
A little... I'm having
a hard time imagiing
the kind of guy you'd
fall for.
What does that
mean?
[chuckle] Nothing!
I‐I didn't offend
you, did I?
Is it odd?
Is what odd?
The tie?
No, I'm talking
about me...
Huh?
[exhale]
(TIGER'S EYE) Excusez‐moi.
Huh?!
Eh, what time
is it now?
Oh, uh...
Time for you to be mine.
[grunt]
[gasp]
One...
Huh?!
Two...
[gasp]
And three!
[scream]
Saori!
[groan]
[scream]
[gasp and growl]
Just who are
you? You're commiting
assault!
Oh, is that
so?
Release me! You're only going to
make your crime worse!
Am I? [laugh]
[straining]
Now just be a good
girl and let me have
a look at your beautiful
dream.
[screaming]
[giggling] Now where are you
hiding, Pegasus?
[laughing]
Hey, where are
you taking me
Chibi‐Usa?
Huh?
Wait, that's...
It's Mamo and
Saori!
(SAORI) [screaming]
[agreed grunts]
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Moon
Crisis Makeup!
[pained moans]
[giggling]
[gasp]
What a shame. Although your
dreams are fueled by a strong
sense of justice, he's not here.
(USAGI) Hold it right there!
[grunt]
How dare you
torment an innocent
woman with such
utter nonsense!
We are the Pretty Guardians!
... Who fight for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
Is that Sailor Moon...?
[grunt]
Come forth, my
Lemures! Pooko, the
Balloon Lady!
[blowing air]
I'm Pooko!
Pushuu! Pushuu, shuu, shuu,
shuu, shuu, shuu! Pushuu!
Pushuu!
[giggling]
No! Get off
of her!
Pooko. I'm leaving the rest to
you.
[collapsing]
This girl's not
cute. What a
shame. Huh?
Chibi Moon...! Ahhh!
Pushuu, pushuu! Pushuu!
Saori! Look out!
Huh?
Uh‐oh!
[gasp] This one is way more
cute!
[grunting]
Pushuu! pushuu!
[screaming]
Huh?
[struggling]
Sailor Moon! Let
go!
[struggling] Uh‐uh!
You're really sacrificing
yourself to save him? That's
just so... so beautiful!
[struggling]
Please! Stop it!
Don't worry. As soon as I kill
her, I'll make sure to kill
you, too. It'll be just like
Romeo and Juliet.
[squeezing]
[gasp] Usako... Usako!
[groaning] "Usako"...?
I see...
[screaming]
[grunt]
[gasp]
Pushuuuuuuuuu!
Usako!
[gasp]
Please, wake up!
[weak breath] I'm okay...
Shuu!
[pained groans]
Ugh! What an ugly thing to do!
Chibi Moon! Do it!
Mhm!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Ugh! This is so frustrating!
[grunting]
Moon Gorgeous Mediatation!
Stage Out!
[gasp]
[panting]
[groaning] Huh?
[weak breath]
Thanks, Usako.
[chuckle]
[sigh]
Hey, Saori.
How'd it go
yesterday?
How'd what go?
Don't play dumb, you know
I'm talking about you and Chiba!
You told him how you feel,
right?
Huh? But why
not?!
Hey...
Huh?
You can have this. I'd hate to
throw it away.
This is...
So, are you
giving up on
him?
'Cuz I certainly don't
think the Police Superintendent
General of Japan would give up.
Oh! I‐I wasn't making fun
of you or anything. I‐It's just
that I‐I really...
[chuckle]
I think I'm pretty okay with
losing a guy to a girl who
protects the world.
Uh... Huh?
Just let go
of him already!
No way! He's
my Mamo!
You're ruining everything!
Shouldn't you be
off playing with
your dog toy?
[frustrated yell]
(USAGI) Mamo, this is awful! Can
you believe Artemis? I think
he's actually cheating on Luna!
(MAMORU) Calm down, Usako. I'm
sure he has a good explaination.
(USAGI) But Mamo!
(MAMORU) W‐What?
(USAGI) He even has a kitten
from this torrid affair!
(MAMORU) Artemis... you old dog,
or cat...
(USAGI) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS: "Artemis is Cheating?
Enter the Mysterious Kitten."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.