(Chibi‐Usa)
I heard that Mamo has been
starting to see a young and
beautiful widow.
(Usagi)
What!? A widow!?
(Chibi‐Usa)
I know Usagi's clumsy and
annoying...
(Usagi)
Chibi‐Usa!
(Chibi‐Usa)
But cheating is still wrong!
(Usagi)
That's true. Wait! The bad guys
are after the widow's beautiful
memories!
In the name of the Moon
we'll punish you!
♪
Oh, hey, Mamoru!
[gasp]
Sorry for the trouble!
Oh, not at all! I
enjoyed coming over.
[gasp]
Just give me a call
if you need me.
Will do! Need a ride?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I can get back on my own.
It is part of the
job, after all.
See ya!
What's going on here?
Hey, Ami, what's up?
Don't play dumb, Mamoru!
That key...!
[gasp]
As Usagi's best friend, I can't
just sit back and ignore what I
saw happen!
Huh?
Uhhh...
(Usagi)
Drive to the Heavens: The Dream
Car Fueled with Love
...and done!
How ya doin' down there?
Great! I'm all finished.
Not too much more to go!
Why don't we take a break?
Sure!
Wow, so it's true!
This is out of
character for her.
Ami? Working part time at
an auto repair shop?
I can't believe it.
[nervous gasps]
[sighs of relief]
You know, it doesn't look like
she's being forced to work
here...
What if she's been
brainwashed or something?!
(Mamoru)
Usako?
[gasp]
Huh?
What are you and the other
girls doing here?
Hi, Mamo!
Usagi! They're falling...
they're falling...!
[screaming]
What are you all doing here?!
Ami, do you know them?
[coughing]
Hold on a second, Mamoru's been
cheating on Usagi!?
[spitting]
Uh, I did not cheat.
...Right?
[giggle]
Hey! What's going on!?
I know that Usagi is
clumsy and possessive, but
cheating is still wrong!
Who's side are you even on!?
Wow, Mamoru, you're the last
person I thought would cheat on
their girlfriend!
Men are just total
pigs, aren't they!
Mhm!
Ugh, come on!
No, you've got it all wrong!
At first I thought he was
cheating, too, but
Natsumi is just a mechanic who
owns this repair shop and was
helping him out.
Seriously?
(Mamoru)
Yeah! It's really simple...
See, what happened was I asked
Natsumi to fix my car, so she
came over to deliver it.
That's all!
[chuckle]
So, then I guess the
keys that Ami saw...
They were just
your car keys.
I'm sorry...
Well, duh! There's no way that
Mamo would ever even think of
cheating on me!
Weren't you the one doubting him
up until a few minutes ago?
Shut up! Stop trying
to cause trouble!
[sticking tongue out]
Oh, by the way, Natsumi, how's
that car you've been working on?
It's almost done, isn't it?
Mhm!
This car's my dream!
Once it's finished, I'm going to
drive it all around town!
Of course, having you around,
Ami, has really helped!
I never would have gotten this
far without your assistance.
Oh, no, you had already
done most of the hard work
before I even got here.
Give yourself more credit!
I mean, you were able to catch
onto basic mechanics pretty
quickly!
And you even fixed some
stuff without my help!
It's almost like you can
understand how the car feels.
You really have a
talent for this!
That's our Ami!
Way to go, girl genius!
Doesn't surprise me at all!
(Usagi)
Woo‐hoo!
All right, ready to put in
some more work?
(Ami)
Yeah!
[sigh]
(Tiger's Eye)
Who's that?
Hm?
Another older woman?
Ew, and she's a grease monkey,
huh? I mean, if that's what
you're into...
[laughing]
You okay?
All right, let me explain
it to both of you.
This one is a woman who has
reached the peak of all other
older women.
So, she's a grandmother?
[groan]
Shut up and listen!
If she were a fish, this woman
would be the fattiest of tuna,
or, the best filet of sole!
Ya get it? She's a widow!
Mmm.. not interested.
Well then, unfortunately it
seems that a jewel is but a rock
to those who don't realize it's
value.
Anyway, I'll be
taking this target.
[tinkering ]
Tomokazu...
What is that?
Nice, huh? The two of us are
gonna fix this beauty up and
make it drivable again!
Are you kidding?
That'll take forever!
Come on, we can do it
if we work together!
Huh?
We're gonna turn our little shop
into the garage of dreams!
We'll be able to repair any car
and be the best auto shop in the
world!
[sigh]
(Usagi)
A widow!?
Yeah, Natsumi and her husband
opened that repair shop together
But unfortunately he passed away
suddenly about three years ago.
It's really heartbreaking,
especially because before he
passed they had promised each
other that they would rebuild
that vintage car together.
I see. That must be why
she's so attached to it.
Don't overwork yourself, okay?
|
You're not planning to stay
there and help her with that car
forever, are you, Ami?
But if I quit before it's
finished, what was the point
in helping her at all?
Natsumi has been running that
garage alone since Tomokazu
died.
So she needs an extra hand!
And besides, I can tell
that that car is filled
with their love, so
getting it to run is something
I'd really like to see.
Hm.
Oh, Ami...
[small gasp]
(Chibi‐Usa)
Hey, Pegasus?
I thought Ami's dream was to
become a doctor...
So why do you think she decided
to help out at that garage?
I'm afraid I don't know.
But, people are allowed to
have more than one dream...
Huh?
Some people wish to make
dreams come true for others.
Whoa, honestly?
Will I be able to have
a dream like that?
Of course you will.
[tires screeching]
(Hawk's Eye)
Excuse me, I'm having
problems with my engine...
...Mind taking a look?
Sure thing.
[gasp]
Tomokazu...
Huh!?
[evil laugh] She completely
fell for my disguise!
Making her mine should be easy!
[gasp] [sigh]
Natsumi!
(Ami)
According to what the doctor
said, Natsumi is suffering from
severe exhaustion.
Oh, wow. She must have been
working long hours all alone.
Well, she won't be able to
work again for a while.
But, the car...
[sad sigh]
What's wrong with me?
Tomokazu's gone...
There's no way he'd
show up like that.
Don't grieve, Natsumi.
[gasp] It's you!
♪Sailor Moon
I lost my parents when I was
very young. I've been so lonely
without them.
Since then, I've been searching
for a woman to share my sadness
with.
That's when I found you!
[gasp]
I promise that you won't have to
live in sadness any longer.
(Hawk's Eye)
Please, sell that repair
shop of yours...
[gasp]
And let's go on a trip
together, right now!
[gasp]
No!
Dammit. Interrupted.
I thought fixing that
car was your dream!
If you just give up on it before
you finish, everyone will be
really disappointed!
Everyone? What
do you mean?
Wait a minute!
Who let you in?
I was seducing... uh, I mean,
talking about our future!
Back off, ascot!
Natsumi, you can't
give up on your shop!
Everyone is over there
doing their best to
help you right now!
[groan]
Hey! Natsumi, what
are you doing!? Wait!
I have a favor to ask you.
Huh?
(Makoto)
Ami, I'm supposed to turn
this clockwise, right?
(Ami)
Uh‐huh!
(Usagi)
I'm just gonna cut this wire and
get it out of my way, cool?
(Ami)
Usagi, calm down!
Don't hit that so hard!
(Usagi)
Nervous giggle
(Rei)
Way to break the
car, Usagi...
(Usagi)
No one asked you, Rei!
Ami...
See, everyone wants the car to
run, so they're all doing their
best to make it work!
Huh?
Making that car run, it's not
just your dream now...
...it's everyone's dream!
[all chattering]
[happy sigh]
(Hawk's Eye)
Is that what this is all about?
Why would you even need to fix
that clunker when I have my
super cool sports car right here
Let's get going now.
I'm sorry...
[gasp]
Look, I don't think I can
go with you after all.
You see, this garage
may be small, but it's
full of big dreams.
I'm staying here.
[happy sigh]
It wasn't a request...
[gasp]
(Natsumi)
[screaming]
Huh?
(Natsumi)
Someone, help!
He, he kidnapped her!
Come on!
Oww...
Get in!
[screaming]
Damn! They don't
give up, do they?
[grunt]
[screaming]
Stop it! Don't
be so reckless!
Are you afraid I'll wreck the
car? Like I give a damn...!
[gasp]
What'd you say?
I knew it! You're
nothing like Tomokazu!
you're the type who doesn't
understand cars at all!
[tires screeching]
I'm only interested
in your dreams, honey!
[gasp]
[running breaths]
[finger snap]
[yell]
[fearful gasp]
[finger snap]
[gasp]
Now, those big dreams of
yours... let's see them!
[gasp]
One...
Two...
...and three!
[screaming]
[fainting sigh]
It's him!
Let's go!
Mercury Star Power Make Up!
(Usagi & Chibi‐Usa)
Moon Crisis Make Up!
(Sailor Mercury)
Hold it right there!
[gasp]
I'm not going to let
you get away with this!
What the‐‐??
(Sailor Moon)
Exactly!
You violated several traffic
laws, and even worse, Natsumi's
precious memories!
We're the pretty guardians...
...who fight for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi‐Moon!
In the name of the Moon,
we'll punish you!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
[evil laugh]
[blowing]
[gasp]
I don't have time to
play with you girls!
Come forth, my Lemures, Ms.
Buranko the Flying Trapeze
Artist Without a harness!
Swinging when there's
no wind... Bura Bura!
Miss Buranko, take care
of these little girls.
Bura Bura!
Bura Bura Bura Bura, catch!
[gasp]
What is this?
[screaming]
[whimper]
We're so high up!
That's not good.
Bura Bura Bura Bura!
Ahhh help!
Nice catch, Sailor Mercury!
Bura Bura Bura Bura!
Sailor Moon, try to swing!
[grunt]
Mercury!
[screaming]
Bura Bura Bura Bura!
You're heavy...
Chibi‐Moon, whatever
you do, don't let go!
We have to do something,
or we're done for!
So lovely, but no
sign of Pegasus!
Humph!
Enough games, Miss Buranko. Make
sure you get rid of all of them!
Bura Bura Bura Bura!
...Bura!
Ahh!
[screaming]
[Tarzan yell]
Tuxedo Mask, you're here!
Sailor Moon! You'e put on
some weight, haven't you?
[groan] Are you not
seeing those two!?
Oh! Sorry...!
Bura Bura Bura Bura!
Here she comes!
If my calculations
are correct...
Bura Bura Bura Bura..!
Snip! Snip? Snip, snip
snip!?
The law of pendulum
motion saved us!
Now's your chance, you two!
‐Right!
Please, Pegasus, protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Bura Bura Bura!
[neigh]
Moon Gorgeous Mediation!
Stage out!
Curses! Bested by little girls!
You ready?
Mhm. Here goes!
[engine failing]
Please let it start!
[gasp]
[engine starting]
No way, it works!
You did it!
[cheering]
[blast]
[coughing]
[gasps]
Uhh...
[laughing]
Thanks so much, Ami!
I'll keep trying to fix this
car, but next time, I won't be
in such a rush!
I have all the time in
the world, after all!
Natsumi!
[laughter]
I, Small Lady, aka Chibi‐Usa,
have decided to train under
Japan's top swordswoman.
(Usagi)
Wait a minute, that's your
teacher? She's just a kid!
(Chibi‐Usa)
She's really strong and cool!
She left home to go on
a training journey!
(Usagi)
Sounds like she's hiding
something!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS,
"Aiming for the Top: The Pretty
Swordswoman's Dilemma."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a messenger
of love.