(Usagi) Guess who I
saw Minako with!
(Chibi‐Usa) An older
guy, right?
(Usagi) Yeah. How
did you know?
(Chibi‐Usa) I saw him! Kinda
cute, with a motercycle and a
"bad boy" look?
(Usagi) What are you talking
about? He was very down‐to‐earth
looking and...
(Both) Wait! That's
not the same guy!
(Usagi) She's two‐timing!
(Usagi) Come on, Minako!
(Both) That's just wrong!
(Chibi‐Usa) Hurry up, Mamo, come
on! Let's go!
(Usagi) Hey!
Whoa, slow down!
No way!
(Mamoru) Hey!
Mamo and I are going to the
movies! He doesn't have time
for you now!
No! He promised to go shopping
with me for the day!
(Mamoru) Hey. Now come on,
you two...
Mamo is coming with me to
see a monster movie!
No way! Shopping!
Movie, movie, movie!
Shopping, shopping, shopping!
No I said a movie!
He's coming shopping,
and that's final!
Huh? Hmm?
(Usagi) Minako!
(Chibi‐Usa) Who's
that? He's cute!
You think he's a boyfriend?
Ooh, wait till I tell
the others about this!
"Storm of Love: Minako's Grand
Two Timing Plan"
(Rei) What?! Minako
has a boyfriend?
I wouldn't kid you.
Wow!
Minako's the last person I
thought would beat me in
the dating race.
Oh come on, Rei, there's nothing
wrong with her being in a
relatinship.
(Both) Well excuse me for
being a total loser.
You guys aren't
total losers.
'Course not.
[Artemis groans]
What is it, Artemis? Is
something wrong?
Tell me, you two, this boyfriend
you saw walking with Mina, what
did he look like?
Well, he was tall...He kind of
looked like the gentle,
sensitive type, and...
(Diana) Not the bad‐boy type?
Long hair, motercycle?
He wasn't like that at all.
He seemed more down‐to‐earth
and...Hm?
[Gasps] Hey, stop
pushing me will you??
Hey! That's not the
boyfriend we saw!
What?
No, but this one's
pretty cute, too!
I knew it.
(Luna) Knew what, Artemis?
What's going on?
(Artemis) [Sighs] You're not
gonna believe this.
Oh! Hi, everyone. Sorry
I'm late.
Minako, who's that
you were with?
Oh, Torajima?
Right now he's a roadie, but
he's going to be a rock star.
We met at a concert and he
asked me out.
Being so beautiful,
is almost a sin.
[Groans]
Wait! Then who was the guy
you were with yesterday?
You mean Takano? He's studying
painting at an arts school.
He said I "inspire his
creative urge."
He's even asked me to "model"
for him, know what I mean? In
the nude.
Like, without any clothes on.
Being so beautiful is,
almost a sin.
Wait, you're seeing both of
them? That means you're...
I believe people call it
"two‐timing."
They're both so different, and
they're both so handsome, and
the best part is they're both so
crazy about me!
(Artemis) She doesn't seem
to be too concerned...
There's nothing like eating
your cake and still having it,
that's what I say! [Laughing]
Master Usagi, what does
"two‐timing" mean?
Well, "two‐timing"
means when you're‐‐
(Artemis) Usagi!
She's too young to hear
about that! [Sighs]
Woah! Minako's on a roll!
[Laughing]
Well, well, if it isn't Tiger's
eye. How's it going with your
target?
Couldn't be better.
(Tiger's Eye) She's being coy.
By tomorrow, she'll be mine .
And how about you?
Oh, I could have had her today.
But it's so much fun watching
you waste your time.
Huh! You haven't got a chance
with her, Pigeon's Eye.
More of a chance than
you have, Tiger Pants!
What's wrong with
these pants?
Everything.
(Fish's Eye) Stop it you two!
Please stop!
I can't stand you fighting over
me! I can't.
(Both) Huh?
I never wanted to
come between you.
Are you kidding? Here's a hot
news flash: we're not fighting
over you.
You're not?
Anyway, where were
we? Oh yeah.
I'll bet you anything that my
technique beats yours in
winning that girl's heart.
Says the guy who's been beaten
by the Sailor Guardians how
many times now?
Hm! And how have you done in
that department? I don't see you
winning any trophies!
Okay, listen! How about the
loser has to leave and never
come back.
You got yourself a deal. Think
you should go start packing.
Boys, boys, come on...
(Both) Shut up and
stay out of this!
This is a competition
between real men!
To see which one
can win the girl!
(Both) The girl Madame Zirconia
chose! That one, there!
(Fish's Eye) That's the
girl you're fighting over?
Wow...Unbelievable.
(Fish's Eye) You have lousy
taste.
Did you say something?
The same thing I continue to
say. It's time to stay focused
on Pegasus and our enemies, not
who you're going out with!
I'm not saying you can't ever
fall in love but‐‐
Yeah, I look cute in this dress,
I think I'll wear this one! For
my date, I mean.
What do you think, Artemis?
Oh, forget it...
(Minako) Artemis?
I totally get it. You
don't have to worry.
Oh, good.
I, Minako Aino, a. k. a. the
Goddess of Love, am going
to seize this moment of romantic
bliss! Yeah!!
[Laughing]
Just meow and walk away.
(Chibi‐Usa) Grownups
are strange.
(Pegasus) What makes
you say that?
Pegasus, how can someone be in
love with two people at the same
time?
You don't think it's possible?
If you and someone else are tied
together by the red strings of
fate, isn't that person the
only one you can love?
Or is it that everyone has
more than one red string?
Some people must experience many
loves in order to find the one
fate has chosen for them.
Wow, really?
[Sighs]
Being a grownup sounds hard.
I should have been there
fifteen minutes ago.
Well, I'll just be fashionably
late, then. After all, a girl
like me's worth waiting for.
Hm.
There he is!
Sorry I'm late!
[Gasps]
I forgot!
Huh?
That's right, I told Torajima
that I'd go on a date with him
today, too.
Minako, you are
so screwed.
Oh, brother...I did
my best to warn her.
(Chibi‐Usa) Artemis?
Uh, Chibi‐Usa!
Worried about Minako, huh?
Worried? No of course
not. I'm just uh‐‐
Uh‐huh...Come on,
you're just a what?
Luna?
Ah jeeze, now
I get it.
Sup?
What are you all
doing here?
I was told that if I came, I'd
get to see an example of
"two‐timing," whatever that
is [Grunts]
Ah‐huh.
What do you mean by that? We're
just worried about Minako, like
you!
[Agreeing]
Mm‐hm.
I can't see!
(Rei) I wonder how she's
gonna get out of this?
Calm down, Minako. Let's just
assess the situation.
Two handsome guys are waiting to
have dates with you.
Opportunities like this
don't happen every day.
That's right! So come on, full
speed ahead! You can make this
work, you know you can!
You're kidding me.
[Gasps]
I think she's finally sold her
soul to the devil!
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Torajima.
I was starting to wonder.
[Panting] Boy am I hot.
I ran to get here.
I'd love a cold drink.
Then let's go get one.
Oh I'd really rather be where
there's lots of sunshine and
fresh air, you know, somewhere
like right here!
Fine with me. I'll
go get us some drinks.
Oh, that'd be great.
I won't go anywhere!
She's as good as mine. Tough
luck, Hawk's Eye.
Takano!
Oh, Minako.
I lost track of the time!
I am such a knucklehead!
So, anyway, I was thinking,
it's such a beautiful day, do
you wanna go see a movie?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey, c'mon,
slow down! What's the rush?
I hate missing the trailers!
They're my favorite part!
Ah!
[Movie Trailer Narration]
Geeze, I can't see a thing.
I hate dark places.
Let's find a seat.
Uh.
[Movie Trailer Narration]
Heh‐hey, this is working out all
right. Holding hands already.
Looks like I win, Tiger's Eye.
[Grunting]
Torajima!
Oh hey, there you are!
Sorry it took me forever
to find the ladies' room.
Here's your drink.
Oh! Thanks a lot.
Whatever this "two‐timing"
thing is, it looks exhausting.
How long do you think she can
keep this up?
Not for very much longer.
(Rei) I don't know, Minako can
be surprisingly powerful in a
tight spot.
[All agree]
(Artemis) It's still
unnacceptable. I won't allow it.
(Artemis) You hear me?!
Time to make
my move.
Minako...
[Gasps]
Nooo!
[Laughing] Hmm.
Hm? What's wrong?
Uh, I just remembered, I have
to call home, sorry. Wait for
me, okay?
[Panting]
What a nightmare!
Now where is Minako?
[Minako] Takano!
Minako! Hey,
where were you?
What are you talking about?
I was sitting right by your side
the whole time!
Which side?
Wow, great movie, wasn't it? I
need to use the restroom, do you
mind?
Uh.
Great, thanks, I
won't be a minute!
[Panting]
[Groaning] I don't think I can
keep this up.
(Artemis) Then don't.
Artemis? Huh? Everyone?
It's not right if you have to
lie to a person in order to go
out with them.
[Sighs]
Don't you think it's about time
to tell them the truth?
Yeah, you're right.
Okay I'll go fix this.
[All] That's the spirit!
After all, two birds in the
bush, is better, than no birds!
Minako, I don't
think that's really‐‐
Not to worry! You're about to
see a different Minako!
But now, I
must be off!
(Usagi) That girl still doesn't
get it.
Good grief, what are
you doing here?
I was about to ask you the same
thing. Look she's my girl. You
can't have her.
Try and stop me!
(Minako) No, don't!
(Both) Minako.
This is all my fault! I don't
want you two fighting because of
me!
Then settle it, Minako!
Decide between us!
Which one of us
do you choose?
Me. I'm the one you want.
I know it's me that you want.
Go on, tell him.
Say it.
Come on, speak up!
Yeah, which is it?
(Both) Well? Well? Well? Well?
Well?
All right! I will no longer hide
the way I truly feel.
(Both) So which is it?
I, I like both of you!
(Both) What?!
That does it,
you little player!
If you think a mere human female
can get away with two‐timing us,
you've got another thing coming!
What the?
You stupid girl!
Not only stupid. What really
pisses me off is that you're
incredibly indecisive.
It can't be! You tricked me! The
whole time!
You weren't being honest!
Oh come on! Look who's talking!
We didn't really
want you anyway.
That's right! It's your dreams
we're interested in.
One!
[Gasps]
Two!
And three!
Ah!
Let's take a look and
be done with it.
Oh no you don't! I'm
getting in there first!
What are you talking
about? This one's mine!
Oh, please don't.
[Fighting]
That's Minako!
Oh, so I guess that's what you
mean by "two‐timing," huh? Is
that what they're doing?
Well, not exactly.
(Both) Out of my way! Out
of my way! Me first!
No, please don't look in there.
You're invading my private
space!
Woah! Never seen that before!
Or that!
[Screaming]
[Panting]
I feel like I need
a shower!
And no Pegasus either. Okay,
let's get rid of this little
hussy.
Hold it right there! How dare
you toy with a romantic girl's
loving heart!
We are the Pretty Guardians of
love and justice!
In the name of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
Oh, the bumpkin
squad's back again.
Come forth, my Lemures, Ms.
Gittanko, the Acrobat of Terror.
And her partner, Bakkonko!
See‐saw!
Saw‐see!
All right, you two,
get rid of them!
Roger! See...Saw!
[Screams]
Hey, watch it! You could've hit
somebody! You don't just go
throwing seesaws around!
See!
Saw!
Uh‐oh.
See!
Huh?
[Screams]
See!
Saw!
[Screams]
Saw‐see!
[Grunts]
Hm! My Lemures made short
work of them that time!
Your Lemures? What
are you talking about?
Just what I said!
It was my Lemures!
It was mine,
don't you get it!
Mina! Psst! Wake up! Mina!
[Grunts] Artemis?
Are you okay?
You idiot! I'll deal with you
once I've finished with these
bumpkins!
You and what army?
What a couple of jerks! How
selfish of them to ruin my
perfect method of two‐timing!
They're gonna pay for that!
[Grunts]
What the?!
Time to transform!
Hmm.
Venus Star Power Make Up!
Now finish them off, you two!
See‐saw! See‐saw! See‐saw!
(Minako) Hold it!
There's another Sailor Guardian
you've forgotten about!
Venus!
Why can't you all show
up at the same time!
You jerks! What you two
did is unforgivable!
Oh yeah? What's
it to you?
I am Sailor Venus! Goddess of
love and beauty!
And now, feel the wrath...
Of my amazing ...
...Crescent Beam Barrage!
[Screams]
(Both) What's she so
upset about?
[Screams]
Now's our chance!
Please Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out!
You'll be sorry!
Not today, but soon!
(Minako) Girls?
(All) Huh?
Sorry.
[Giggling]
Rats! I thought I had
it in the bag this time.
Looks like we both came up empty
so let's just call it a draw.
Fine with me.
Wait. If you both lost, doesn't
that mean you both have to go
away?
(Both) What was that?
Just kidding, can't you
boys take a joke?
Mina, we should go.
The others are waiting.
Mm‐hm.
Artemis?
Hm?
I can't belive I let those guys
play me like that. I feel so
dumb.
From what I could see, you had
them going pretty good too.
Anyway, maybe that's how it
really works. Only after
experiencing many different
relationships...
...do you find your one true
love.
Thanks, Artemis.
Okay, let's go!
I bet he's right. Everyone I
meet, they're all leading up
to that one special someone
I'll find some day.
(Usagi) I wonder, what if
we weren't always together?
(Mamoru) What do you mean?
(Usagi) What would happen to our
feelings if we were seperated
for twenty years?
(Mamoru) Who knows?
(Usagi) I'd make you a pot of
pot‐au‐feu to eat when you
return. Wouldn't that be so
romantic?
(Mamoru) Ew, twenty‐year
old pot‐au‐feu?
(Usagi) That's not what I meant!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"The Secret Mansion: A Menu of
Love for You."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.