(CHIBI‐USA) Wait, the author of
The Moon Night Pegasus...
(USAGI) ...is Mako's friend?!
[happy squeal] Let's get her
autograph!
(CHIBI‐USA) Usagi, it's the bad
guys again!
(USAGI) [groan] If you're
thinking of peeking into that
young author's pure dreams,
then...
In the name
of the moon...
...we'll punish you!
(USAGI) The Moon Night Pegasus
is such a beautiful story, isn't
it?
The tragic tale of
unrequited love between a
Pegasus and a human woman...
[deep, weepy breath] It makes me
cry every time I read it!
Oh, I've read that
one. It's pretty obvious
why it sold over a million
copies.
Uh‐huh!
Usagi read an actual novel?
Don't you usually only read
things with pictures? So who
bribed you?
Hey, that's not very nice, Rei.
You probably haven't even read
the book, have you?
Uhhh?!
Seriously, I must have
cried at least ten
times when I read
it.
One day, I
hope I'll fall
that deeply in
love...
Me too. I
was surprised at
how moving the
story was.
Even Ami's read it? Then it
must be an amzing novel. Why am
I behind?!
Wow... I wonder if the author
knows the same Pegasus I do?
Oh?
[gasp]
Huh?
(USAGI) Makoto's Friendship: The
Girl Who Admired Pegasus
[giggle] Yeah, I'm totally fine.
This might be hard to believe,
but I actually used to be
classmates with the author of
that book, Tomoko Takase...
...before I transfered
schools.
What?!
(LUNA) Then that means
she's the same age as you and
Usagi.
AUTHOR PHOTO
There's definitely a
noticeable difference in
talent.
[grumble] Watch it kitten!
But more importantly; why
didn't you tell us before that
you were friends with a
celebrity, Mako?
I thought if I'd mentioned it, I
probably would have sounded like
I was bragging about knowing
someone famous...
...even if I didn't mean to.
[nervous laugh] Well it
definitely makes a lot of
sense when you put it that
way...
Usagi would've told
everyone about something
like that for
sure.
Mm‐hm!
If you don't
have anything
nice to say...
It all began with a suggestion
I made. I wanted her to try
sending one of her stories to a
magazine.
I'd read her manuscript. Then,
I'd tell her what I thought.
My words encouraged Tomoko and
she continued writing.
Her hard work paid off and she
released her debut novel, The
Moon Night Pegasus.
(CHIBI‐USA) That means we're
able to read Tomoko's amazing
novel...
...because you're the one who
discovered her talent and helped
inspire her, Mako!
Yeah, I guess
I did, huh?
So much for
not wanting to
sound like you're
bragging...
But that was a
long time ago. Tomoko's
a best‐selling author now.
I got so distracted with
personal stuff...
...that I still haven't had a
chance to really congratulate
her on her accomplishments.
Oh, Mako...
Hm...
I know! How about we all go over
to Tomoko's place next Sunday so
we can get her to autograph our
books?
Uh, but...
[giggle] Come on, it'll
be fine!
And I'm sure that Tomoko
would love to see you
again after all this time!
Wait a minute,
Usagi. What if
the others don't
want to...
Oh! I wanna
meet her, too!
Uhhh?
I'd absolutely love to
meet the person who wrote this
beautiful story. Please, Mako.
Let's go!
[sigh]
Mmm, why not? It will be nice to
see her again.
[giggles] Yay for us!
(ZIRCONIA) You three...
Are you ever going to be
competent enough to capture
Pegasus?
But Madame Zirconia...
Be quiet!
[cowering]
If only you three fools put as
much care into your useless
brains as you do your flashy
apperances.
Welcome back, Zircon.
Try this girl next!
Huh?
Oh, I know this girl.
She's that best selling author,
isn't she?
Yeah, I've read her
book. It was the most
hilariously awful thing I've
ever laid my eyes on!
I know! Didn't you think the
part where the Pegasus gives his
life for the girl was especially
lame?
(ZIRCONIA) Enough!
[startled yelps]
Her story of Pegasus has
captivated people's hearts.
This writer, Tomoko Takase...
it's possible that she may know
something about Pegasus.
In that case, please, leave this
one to me.
So, a young, female author who
writes ephemeral love stories...
This target will be like putty
in my hands.
[laugh]
Wow! Who would have
thought that you would be
friends with the famous author,
Tomoko Takase?
As they say, "Don't
judge a friend, they
might know a celebrity."
Yup, no. No
one says that.
[giggle] I bought an extra
copy of the book just for her
to sign today!
What an amateur. If
you want to do it right, you
need to buy at least three
copies.
[gasp]
why three?
That way, there's one to read at
home, another to keep in mint
condition...
...and the last one is
just for showing off to
people, of course.
[giggle]
(AMI MIZUNO) Oh, Rei...
(LUNA) Some
things never
change do they?
Hmmm?
This place brings back a lot of
memories...
Tomoko's house is right
around the corner, just up
ahead.
[chuckle]
Master Makoto
seems happy.
Of course she
is. She's about
to get her
booked signed!
[groans] That's
not why at all...
Soon, I'll be meeting the person
who wrote this book...
[Editors chttering/begging]
Huh?
What's going on?
[chuckle]
Young, female authors have
plenty of fans of the same
sex...
...but hansome, male fans like
me are a rarity. She'll be mine
in no time!
[Editors chattering and
pleading]
Huh?
No way! I have to compete
against those guys?!
They won't beat me!
[more pleading]
Excuse me, coming
through!
Who do you
think you are?!
(TIGERS EYE) Get your dirty paws
off me!
Do you know how much I paid for
this suit?!
What's all this about?
None of us can
get in contact with
Tomoko.
She's way past
the deadline for
her manuscript.
Oh no!
She probably ran
away because she
couldn't handle the
pressure.
[grunt]
Tomoko would never
do that!
Okay...
Writing novels is
everything to her.
It's all she
has!
[gasps]
Mako, wait!
[relieved sigh] Tomoko!
Is that... Mako?
[sniffling]
[panting] I knew I'd
find you here.
Just like back
then.
Why are you hiding back here?
Your dream was to be a writer.
Are you just gonna throw all
that away?
I can't write.
What?
I'm useless. I can't even write
a sentence. The words just don't
come to me anymore.
Tomoko...
I'll never be able
to write a story better
than The Moon Night
Pegasus.
I don't even
have a dream
to work towards
anymore!
Wait! Tomoko!
[laugh]
So it seems the
young author has
a case of writer's block.
This is perfect. I would use
this chance to make her mine...
But... I need to go change my
pants...
Is she okay?
Yeah, she is...
I think.
What happened to you, Tomoko?
You used to love writing so
much.
(BOY A) You want it? Come get
it!
[cocky laugh]
[gasp]
[laughing]
Stop it! Give
it back!
Here it is!
[laugh] It's over here
now!
Stop! Please!
(MAKOTO) Hey!
Huh?
Wha‐‐?!
It's Makoto!
We're in big
trouble now!
Let's get out
of here!
Oh, um... Thank
you...
Instead of thanking me,
you should have chased
after them and kicked their
butts.
Hey, wait. Do
we... go to
the same school?
Uh huh. Same class.
Huh?! Right, sorry. I just
transferred here, so I don't
know everyone yet.
Uh? Hey, is this homework?
No, it's not.
Hm?
It's... my manuscript...
Manuscript?
[gasp] Give it back!
Please!
But I wanna
read it.
Well, I just finished it
and I wasn't really planning
to show it to anyone yet.
Stop talking.
[sigh] It's good.
Huh?
I'm really liking
it a lot so far.
I may not look
it, but I love reading. And
honestly, your story has me
totally hooked.
Oh, um... Thank you,
but... You're just
being nice.
Look, I don't give
empty compliments to
strangers.
Well, let me know
if you write
more, okay?
[gasp] I will!
[grunt]
[kick]
[gasp]
Hello!
Mako... Thank you.
Oh, I see.
So you like
the athletic type,
huh?
[nervous gasp]
When I watch him
play... I jsut get all kinds
of inspiration for stories.
He knows...
...right?
Well, no. He's just so popular.
I bet he probably doesn't even
know I exist.
I've got an idea! What
if you tried submitting your
novel to a magazine or
something?
Huh?
That way, more people
can read it!
If you get your novel
published and everyone
starts talking about it, then
he'll have to notice you!
But what if
I fail...
You've got this.
I believe in
you, Tomoko.
[chuckle]
Mako...
(LUNA) Hey, where's Chibi‐Usa?
Huh?
You don't think
she...
[crying]
THE MOON NIGHT PEGASUS
TOMOKO TAKASE
BOOK SIGNING
IGARASHI
BOOKSTORE
Thanks so much.
Next in line,
step on up.
Hello there!
[gasp]
[shocked gasp]
It doesn't matter what I write.
No one understands what I
actaully feel... No one...
(CHIBI‐USA) Tomoko!
Huh?
I've seen Pegasus too!
It was a beautiful horse with
wings, exactly how you described
it in your book!
Reading about it made me happy!
I couldn't believe you shared
the same dream as me!
The same dream?
And that's why I
really want to read
more of your stories,
Tomoko!
[gasp]
[crying] But... I can't! I just
can't write!
(MAKOTO) So that's it?
Huh?
You're gonna
to give up
just like that?
Mako...
Master Usagi!
Shh... How about we let Mako
handle this.
You used to hide your stories
inside your desk beacuse you
were too embarrassed to let
people read your work.
Do you really
want to be that
coward again?!
[gasp]
Remember the commitment you
once made to yourself?
You said that even if you had
only a single reader, you'd
always finish your story for
them!
The dreams you
write about don't
belong to just you anymore!
[gasp] She's right.
[gasps]
[chuckle]
[happy sigh]
[chuckles]
So how has
your latest manuscript
been coming along,
Miss Takase?
[gasp]
Huh?
You are...?
Oh, please forgive
me.
My name is
Taiga.
I'm from Dead Publishing and
I've been assigned as your new
editor from this point on.
Pleased to meet you.
DEAD PUBLISHING
EDITORIAL DEPARTMENT
ZUAI TAIGA
(TOMOKO) Dead Publishing?
I've never heard of it.
A writer who keeps to herself
falls madly in love with her
handosme editor.
Now... Allow me to burn your
heart witrh the blazing fire of
my love!
[gasp]
[chuckle]
[scream]
(MAKOTO) Jupiter Star Power Make
Up!
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Moon
Crisis Make Up!
[panting]
[chuckle]
[gasp and scared groan]
A girl like you must be filled
with plenty of wonderful dreams.
May I see if I'm right?
One...
[scream]
Two...
Three!
[scream]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
[dodging]
Who are you?
I'm not gonna let you lay a
finger on Tomoko!
Say's who?!
(USAGI) Says we!
How dare you pose
as an editor to prey
on a young author's
dreams!
We're the Pretty Guardians...
... who fight for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
In the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
It's you again!
Come forth, my Lemures!
Tenko, the Deadly Time Bomb
Escape Magician!
Tenko!
Alright then. I'll
leave them to
you.
Tenko.
Okay!
Time to wrap you up in chains!
[grunt]
[gasps]
Ahhh!
[screams and grunts]]
Oh No!
Supreme...
(LUNA) Wait, Jupiter!
If you do
that, then you'll
all...
...Thunder!
Huh?
Ahhh!
[coughing]
...end up frying yourselves.
[chuckle] Serves them right.
Now where was
I...
Leave her alone!
[grunt]
[laughing] So beautiful! But
where's Pegasus?
[gasp]
I only came all this
way because you were
Madame Zirconia's personal
pick...
Tenko, dear. Please
dispose of them
all, would you?
Tenko!
Now, setting timer!
Huh?
What the heck
is that thing?
A time bomb. Two minutes and
KABOOM! Kay?
No, not okay!
You've got to
be kidding!
[chukle] Do your best
to escape. Tenko!
[struggling]
[grunting] Dammit!
[laughing] One minute!
[struggling]
[smirking]
[gasp]
Huh?
Huh?!
Chains aren't fitting for pretty
girls. The only things that
should be chained are villians
and vicous animals.
Thank you, Tuxedo Mask!
I think this belongs to you!
[grunts]
[dodging]
Chibi Moon! Do it!
Please Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
It's a... Pegasus...
[struggling]
I'm gonna blow you all away!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage Out!
Huh?! Oh, forget it!
You okay, Tomoko?...
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Mako! I saw
it! A real
Pegasus!
Huh?
I'm still able
to have beautiful
dreams.
So, I can
still write...
Hm. Actually, I
want to write!
Only, this time, it's not for
myself,... it's for everyone!
[chuckles]
Well, good luck!
Goodbye!
Wait, Mako!
Huh?
When my new novel is done, will
you read it first?
Hmph. I'd be honored. You can
always count on me to be your
first reader, got it?
[chuckle] Yeah.
PEGASUS FANTASY
TOMOKO TAKASE
Dedicated to my dearest frined,
Makoto...
And to all the dreamers out
there.
(CHIBI‐USA) Hey, am I annoying?
(USAGI) Well, you have an
attitude and eat people's
snacks, and your voice is high,
and you have a daddy complex‐
(CHIBI‐USA) Shut up Usagi!
I'm just wondering how it's
possible to like someone and not
get along with them. Humans can
be so complicated...
(USAGI) Isn't that topic a
little mature for somoene your
age?!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Connecting Hearts: Chibi‐Usa
and Pegasus"
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.