[piano music]
[sigh]
(Chibi‐Usa)
Hi, Ami!
Ahh!
Oh, you're here early!
Actually, we've been
here for quite a while.
Oh, hi, guys.
This is no time to daydream.
The enemy has been gaining
strength and growing more
active, so we need you to stay
focused.
Right, I'm sorry!
By the way, Ami... What's
this notebook for?
[gasp]
Yoink!
Something tells me...
It's not for studying.
Rei!
"My soul yearns to gaze into
your captivating eyes
forever..."
Ooooh!
It's not what you
think! ' It's a...
It's a what?
Y'see, it's...
It's a love letter!
Aw, she's blushing!
[chatter]
[laughing & giggling]
♪
(Usagi)
True Power Explodes: Ami's
Melody of the Heart
(Rei)
"Online networking?"
Yes. This is original music I
found when I was searching
the net.
[piano music]
It sounds wonderful!
I love it!
It's so relaxing.
When I listen to this melody, it
fuels my spirit and stirs my
imagination.
I was so inspired, I couldn't
stop myself from writing down
lyrics for the music.
You were song writing!
That's great, but I still
don't get it. What is
"online networking"?
[groan]
What'd I say? Tell me!
Oh, come on! Everybody
knows what that stuff is.
Usagi, it's simple! "Online
networking" is when a person
is networking online!
Gee, thanks for your help.
She means it's a way for people
to socialize with each other
through their computers.
People not only post their
music, they share all sorts of
creative work and compositions.
Listening to this makes me
wonder... what's the songwriter
like.
All I know is that the
music credit says "T. N."
Well, one thing's for sure: A
guy who writes a piece like
that has to be handsome.
Hold on. The composer
might not even be a man.
‐Aw, where's the fun in that?!
Oh...
We wa to fantasize about a guy
who can write great music.
Sorry for ruining your fun.
‐Ami, don't you agree?
Uhh, sure [nervous laugh]
(Chibi‐Usa)
I'd like to meet him...
...the person who
wrote this melody.
[sigh] Yeah, me too.
(Amazon Quartet)
Come back here!
Why're you running away?
Yeah! Palla‐Palla will
be nice to you! Promise!
I bet you'd be delicious cracked
and served sunny‐side‐up.
[giggle]
I disagree...
...we should deep fry him!
So cute!
Hm?
[screams]
You tiresome fools!
I have had it with your pranks!
Instead of wasting time fooling
around, hurry up and find me
the Golden Mirror!
Here!
The hell is this?
(Palla‐Palla)
It's out of focus...
Maybe if we squint we
can make it out.
Don't even bother! We'll
never tell who it is!
Why you...!
I order you to leave here at
once and find that mirror!
[screams]
(Palla‐Palla)
Owww...
(Jun‐Jun)
Damn it! That old hag
sure didn't hold back.
(Cere‐Cere)
And my complexion is ruined.
How're we supposed to search
with this lousy photo?
Here, let Palla‐Palla
make it better.
Random Orb!
Hm?
Well...?
‐Well!?
I hear music playing, so the
target must be a musician!
So useless !
(Jun‐Jun)
Who's to blame?
Uhh...!
(Palla‐Palla)
It's not Palla‐Palla's fault.
(Cere‐Cere)
It was Ves‐Ves who broke Zircon.
Now hold on a minute!
This job's all yours!
[piano music]
(Ami)
Dear T. N., I introduced your
composition to my friends
today.
They all loved it,
just like I do...
I was so inspired by it that
I've started working on lyrics.
I hope you don't mind. I just
want my words to be worthy of
your wonderful melody...
Yours truly, Ami.
[sigh] Writing lyrics is
harder than I thought...
[doorbell chime]
Coming!
It's from Dad!
[gasp] It's beautiful!
(Thinking)
It's funny how Dad always
sends his sketches instead of
letters when he travels.
...There are no words
attached to it...
...But I can feel so much
warmth and love from him.
...The drawings themselves
are Dad's message to me.
...Alright! I can do this!
After all, I am the daughter
of a creative artist!
...I'll give it my best!
(Minako)
Wow... Did you really stay up
all night long to finish writing
these lyrics?
I put my heart into them but I
can't tell if they're any good
at all.
They are! You
did a great job.
You shared your true
feelings in this song.
You think so?
Come on, you're wasting
everyone's time. Hurry up
and give me a turn!
What do you mean
by wasting time!?
You really think you can
offer Ami any advice?
Of course! It just takes
some artistic instincts!
Then it's too bad that the only
instincts you have are primeval!
[growl]
Oh, yeah!? Well,
you're, you're medieval!
Maybe I'm not cut out for
writing song lyrics.
Calm down!
Diana!
Hello, everybody!
What is it?
I've made a huge discovery!
Look in there!
[piano music]
That song...
It's the same melody
you found online!
Wait a minute,
does that mean...
He's T. N.?
[piano music]
(Thinking)
That's definitely the melody.
I guess he's the target.
♪ Sailor Moon
See you next week!
(Usagi)
Excuse me?
Can I help you?
Well, um...
Just go for it, Ami!
Um, I‐‐ you see...
[groans]
Aw, c'mon! You can do it!
I um... Your music. I've heard
it before. Online, actually.
My music?
Yes, it was wonderful!
It touched my heart.
I liked your work so much, I
tried to write lyrics for it.
...I don't know if you'll
like them, but...
Hold on. Is your name Ami?
Yes!
I'm Nishino.
Toshiyuki Nishino.
Does that mean you're "T. N."?
That's me! I see your name all
the time on the music forum.
I've always wondered what
you were like. I'm so glad
we finally got to meet!
Hmmm?
Oh! Please, forgive me! I
was so excited that I...
You all must be Ami's friends.
On the chat forum, she's
told me a lot about you.
Oh, is that right?
What've you been telling
him about us, Ami?
[gasp] No! Nothing bad!
All I said was...
Hey, guys...
Huh??
I know it's a little late, but
would you like to visit my
studio?
I want to introduce
you to my partner.
We'd love to. Thanks!
[piano music]
That was lovely.
You did a great job.
Let's stop here for today.
Okay, Ms. Kyoko.
I'll see you next week!
Be careful on your
way home, okay?
Hi, Mr. Nishino.
Nice to see you.
Likewise, nice to see you too.
Get home safely.
Everyone, this is my songwriting
partner who shares the studio
with me... Kyoko.
Kyoko this is Ami. You know, the
one from the music forum.
Oh sure! Hi, how do you do?
Uh‐uh, nice to meet you.
Bummer. Looks like this
one's got a girlfriend.
[gasp]
‐Huh?
You can ignore her. She's
fine. It's nothing!
It must feel great to meet the
person you've been wondering
about this whole time.
I have a feeling fate
is at work here!
Hey, come on.
Don't tease me.
So do you give
piano lessons, too?
Composing songs is a hard
way to make a living.
The two of us teach piano and
perform at nightclubs around
town to make ends meet.
That sounds like a
difficult lifestyle.
I guess so, but it's worth it
when you have a dream like we
do.
A dream?
Yes! Our dream is to become
composers whose music is
played around the world.
It's quite a goal... maybe we
should be more realistic?
There isn't any harm
in us dreaming big.
Plus, great music
knows no boundaries!
[chuckle]
(Thinking)
What on earth was I thinking!
I was foolish to think I could
write for truly creative people
like them.
(Nishino)
...And you, Ami?
Huh!?
Do you have a dream? To become a
lyricist? Or a pianist maybe?
Uhh...
Ami's dream is to be a
doctor! Isn't that right?
Yup! And she's always studying
hard to learn everything she
can!
Really?
You must be very smart.
She sure is!
(Thinking)
But I don't know a
thing about songwriting.
I never should have
tried to write lyrics.
Ami, can I read your lyrics for
my music? I'm excited to see
what you wrote.
Show it to him, Ami.
Yeah, come on.
I can't!
[gasp]
There are still parts that I
want to make changes to.
But I'll bring it over next
time. I'm so sorry!
But Ami...
[gasp]
Wait, come back!
Thanks for having us over.
We've gotta go!
What happened?
[gasps]
Hey!
Forget those girls. Why
don't you play for me?
Ami! What's the matter!?
I can't show him my lyrics.
But, why not?
Come on, you put so much
heart and soul into them...
(Ami)
It was a mistake to
think I could do this!
They're real musicians. They
fill their music with such
passion...
I was just writing
lyrics for fun.
I would be
insulting their work.
I'm no artist!
But Mr. Nishino's music inspired
you! The lyrics you wrote are
genuine and full of feeling!
So what!? They mean nothing!
Wait!
That's not true.
[distant scream]
[gasps]
(Usagi)
Come on, you put so much heart
and soul into them...
(Makoto)
The lyrics you wrote are genuine
and full of feeling!
[Sigh]
(Diana)
Master Ami!
[gasp]... Diana!
It's Mr. Nishino!
What? What happened!?
Kyoko!
Who are you!?
Who, me? I'm just a good
little girl passing through
the neighborhood...
...who wants you.
[grunt]
What the‐‐!?
Now then, time to take a good
look at your dream mirror!
Orb Shot!
Argh!
Aww, this isn't the
Golden Mirror!
That's what I get for relying on
a blurry photograph.
(Sailor Moon)
Hey! What do you
think you're doing!?
The autumn leaves are a symphony
of color. But you're a sour
note.
We're the Pretty Guardians...
...Who fight for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi‐Moon!
And we are the Sailor Guardians!
In the name of the Moon...
We'll punish yoU!
Aren't you embarrassed about the
corny stuff you have to say?
Course not!
You should be embarrassed.
We're the good guys!
Oh, yeah? Well you still
sound like idiots.
Let's get this over with.
Come forth, my Lemures!
Kero‐Kero Girl, the
Dream‐Eating Frog!
Do‐re‐mi‐fa‐so‐la‐ti‐do.
‐It's so cute!
Remember: Tadpoles
are... frog spawn!
[screams]
Oh...
Ribbit‐Ribbit‐Ribbit‐Ribbit!
Hey, where are you going?!
Don't worry. Ribbit!
Power up complete!
(Ami)
What's going on!?
Ami!
Mr. Nishino! You're gonna
stop and leave right now!
Shut up! I can't stand it when
people try to tell me what to
do.
[screams]
What happened?
Where the heck are we?
(Ves‐Ves)
You're inside a computer.
[gasps]
Hello!
Let us out of here!
Sure, after I do my job.
Kero‐Kero Girl, gobble
up that guy's dream!
Roger that! Ribbit!
No, please don't!
Oh, be quiet.
[screams]
No, stop!
It's meal time!
[chomp]
Noooo!
I failed to save Mr. Nishino.
At this rate, I can't even call
myself a Guardian.
I wish I had more power... The
power to save everyone!
(Voice)
Mercury... Sailor
Mercury...
Who said that? Who
called my name?
(Voice)
Feel it...The true power that's
been inside you all this time.
Who are you?
I am you.
Remember your dream. Remember
how you felt the first time you
heard Mr. Nishino's music.
My dream...?
Yes... And remember the sketches
your father always sends you ‐‐
how they make you feel.
That's right...!
What's important is... my
pure, genuine feelings.
Now, open up your heart. Let
your passion and dreams flow.
Give me the courage to release
my true feelings, my true
power, So I can protect my
friends!
Mercury Crystal Power Make Up!
♪
I can feel it! A new
melody of water...
And a harp's music
playing in my heart.
This must be my new power!
Mercury Aqua Rhapsody!
Huh...?!
What!?
[grunts]
Huh... You escaped from my
cyber‐prison?! How's that
possible?
Playtime is over. And you're
going offline!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
[neigh]
♪
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage out!
(Ves‐Ves)
That was impressive, ladies.
Well, I guess I'm
done for today.
See ya!
(Sailor Moon)
Ami?
Here... your lyrics.
You guys... thank you.
(Usagi)
What do you think of
Ami's lyrics?
I don't know what to say...
Is it 'cause they're bad?
No, it's the opposite!
Huh!?
I think your lyrics
are fantastic!
They're the perfect match
for the piece I wrote.
It's like his music brought out
a passion deep inside of you. I
can tell you love this music
very much.
You're right. We can't
let this go to waste.
Thank you, Ami.
You've given us a
wonderful gift!
Sure!
Congrats, Ami!
[chuckle]
(Ami)
My friends helped me remember
something important today:
Being true to my feelings is
the key to making my dreams
a reality...
♪
(Usagi)
Rei, are you always going
to be a shrine maiden?
(Rei)
It's hard to say. After all, I
do have lots of other dreams.
(Usagi)
Oh, yeah?
(Rei)
With my beauty, staying stuck in
a place like this would deny the
world my gifts.
That's why I have dreams of
gaining international success!
(Usagi)
Yeah, that's more
like the Rei I know.
(Usagi)
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Flames of Passion: Mars's
Raging Super Attack."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.