(Usagi) Ooh, a dance party!
(Chibi‐Usa) Why's Mako
acting so strange?
(Usagi) It's called love at
first sight! But wait, that
guy...
(Chibi‐Usa) Yeah! I saw him
dancing with lots of other
girls!
(Usagi) What a jerk! How dare he
toy with Mako's feelings and
cheat on her like that!
In the name of the Moon...
(Both) We'll punish you!
"Destined Partners? Makoto's
Innocence."
Bah.
The Sailor Guardians have
defeated you. Time and Time
again.
Tell me, do the three of you
think you'll ever manage to
capture Pegasus, or is that
asking too much?
With all due respect,
Madame Zirconia...
We've used the Dream Mirror to
peer into the beautiful dreams
of so many humans, I've lost
count!
And we haven't been able to find
the slightest trace of Pegasus
in any of them!
Good grief. That's the problem
with you young people today, you
don't know how to think for
yourselves.
(Zirconia) If what you're doing
isn't working, then use your
heads and come up with something
else...
(Zirconia) ...you worthless
good‐for‐nothings!
Or I'll find someone
who will.
[Sighs]
Well, it's easy for her to say.
How does she expect us to find
something that just isn't there?
Exactly, especially when all
we've got to work with are
miserable targets like these.
Yeah, a bunch of silly, lovesick
college co‐eds. So boring.
Fine. I'll take them
all myself, then.
What do you mean?
What are you up too?
A whole new approach.
I've been thinking, why waste my
spectacular good looks seducing
one girl at a time,
when I can have dozens of them
swooning over me?
Quantity over quality, huh? Even
a lousy marksman can get lucky,
is that it?
[Coughing] Yuck!
I hate carrots!
You think you can handle that
many at once? Yeah, good luck
with that.
It's called using my head, but
of course, you wouldn't
understand that. Watch and
learn, losers.
Huh?
What's with him?
Beats me.
Huh?
He dropped one.
[Laughing/Talking]
You think I went a little
overboard with this dress?
Oh, no! Not at all!
That's right, this is a college
event,
and the competition is
cut‐throat, so you've got to
stand out if you want to catch
the biggest fish.
Hey! So you all made it!
Oh, hi Mamo!
You're all dressed to the nines.
Could it be for the dance party
in the gym, I wonder?
Yup, you guessed it!
We can't wait!
Our college dance party is
becoming known to the general
public as an unofficial
match‐making event.
Yeah, 'cuz you never know if
the next person you dance with
might end up being that special
someone.
By the end of it, a lot of dance
partners are serious couples,
and some even get married.
Did you say married?
That's right! Now that you
mention it, brother, I seem to
recall that's how you hooked
Reika.
[Gasps]
Yeah?
[Grunts] Not you too,
Mamoru!
Hey, we're wasting
time, girls!
Yeah! Our fateful encounters are
in there waiting for us!
[Laughing] Yeah, c'mon, Mamo!
C'mon hurry up!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Don't hurt him, Usagi.
My fateful encounter...
You're not looking
very happy, Mako.
Well, it's just that when you're
tall like me, no one ever asks
you to dance, but I'm used to
it.
I'll ask you to dance,
if you want.
Why not?
[Laughing]
Whoah!
(Chibi‐Usa) Look at Mako go!
Woo!
(Tiger's Eye) That tall one's
not bad, not bad at all.
Unfortunately, she isn't one of
the beautiful dreamers I'm
after.
Still, there's no reason I can't
use her to get the ball rolling.
Is it over already?
What happened?
Coming through, excuse me.
May I have this dance?
Huh? You want
to dance with me?
What do ya know.
Where did he come from?
Am I dreaming? Dancing never
felt like this before.
(Makoto) [Sighs] Wouldn't it be
wonderful if this was my fateful
encounter.
[Sighs]
All right, girls. All right.
Calm down. One at a time!
Look at this. I threw in a sprat
and caught a whale. Hm! See what
I'm capable of when I put my
mind to it.
Scuze me?
Oh, the sprat. Hello.
Do you think you might want
to dance with me again?
I'm all booked up.
But maybe later.
Ooh, that is...
Definitely love at first sight.
She's fallen
hard, all right.
[Sighs]
Say what? You're kidding, so
Mako's just been waiting around
the gym ever since?
Yeah, she said she didn't want
to go anywhere in case that
blond guy came back and wanted
to dance with her again.
You know Mako, when she falls
for someone, she falls all the
way. It's like a bottomless pit!
Chibi‐Usa said she was going to
try and go get her.
I think maybe we should
all go check on her.
And that concludes our dance
party for today. Thank you all
for coming and we hope everyone
will join us again, tomorrow.
[Talking]
[Gasp] That must be him!
Oh. Why are you still here?
Hey! Watch your attitude! You're
not very nice!
Mako's been waiting forever to
dance with you!
Well, that's a problem. You see,
I promised all these other
lovely ladies that I'd dance
with them.
Oh, I'll wait!
But Mako...
Yeah! It's all right. I can wait
till you're done.
Hmm. I don't have time to waste
on a girl who's not on my list
of beautiful dreamers.
Well, maybe later.
Hey, it's that
blond guy!
Did he just leave you? Wow,
that's pretty cold. What a jerk!
No, I admire him for not wanting
to break the promises he made to
those girls.
Besides, he remembered who
I was and everything.
Yeah, I guess that's true,
but...
Oh well, the dancing is over for
the day so how about we all just
head home.
Nah, you all go on ahead, I
think I'll wait. Just in case he
comes back here again.
Oh, Mako...
Pegasus?
I don't understand how Mako can
be so crazy about that guy
already. She only met him today.
Where feelings are concerned,
time is irrelevant. If the right
person came along, you might
fall in love at first sight too.
Huh?
I guess so.
When you fall deeply in love,
you become blind to everything
else around you.
(Usagi) What?
Are you sure?
What's the matter?
It's Mako! She still hasn't
come back home yet.
Huh?
Mako!
Usagi, what's up?
(Usagi) Mako, why are
you still here?
I can't possibly go home while
there's even a chance he might
come back. I'd never forgive
myself if I missed him.
But you don't even know who he
is or where he's from.
True. But that's why I want to
see him again.
But Mako...
This is why I came! It was my
dream to wear a beautiful dress
and dance with my Prince
Charming.
(Makoto) And my dream came true!
If I let my Prince Charming get
away now, I'll regret it for the
rest of my life.
(Ami) You'll really regret
catching a cold by staying out
here in the rain.
Huh?
What are you all...?
(Rei) Here, use this.
We're gonna wait
here with you.
Ooh, yeah! Great idea! We'll
hang out together and tell
stories all night long!
Sorry, everyone.
Hey, no need to be sorry, Mako.
Good luck!
Let's leave this to the others
and go on home, all right?
Mhm!
[Talking]
(Announcer) Ladies and
gentlemen. The winning title of
our 12th Annual Beauty Pageant
goes too...
None other than contestant
number thirteen, Miss Nanami
Uokawa!
That's me! That's me! Oh my
gosh, I'm so happy you made the
right choice!
Hold on! Wait a minute!
Get over here, Fish's Eye! What
the hell do you think you're
doing?
[Laughing]
Oh my gosh!
Wow, I totally forgot all
about you, Tiger's Eye.
Huh?
Yeah, Mako better eat
something or she just might
collapse form hunger.
Huh?
Hmm.
Here.
What is that?
You dropped this from that huge
stack of photos back at the bar,
so I figured that I'd better
come deliver it to you.
But then I got distracted by all
these cute boys here and I
forgot all about it.
That's so typical of you, Fish's
Eye. [Gasps] It's that girl!
You know her?
Sort of.
How's it going, by the way?
After all that boasting about
what a stud you are, it would be
kind of embarrassing if you came
up short.
It's going great, as
a matter of fact.
I can't keep the girls off me,
they're like flies to honey. I
can nail twenty of them at a
time, if I want to.
[Growls]
[Groans]
Good for you. Well, while you're
at it, why don't you show her a
good dream, too?
[Chuckles] I will.
He's a womanizer!
That's unforgivable! This guy's
nothing but a lousy playboy!
He should be taught a lesson
for toying with poor Mako's
feelings!
Hmm!
They're gone!
Hmm. Huh?
I can't tell you how touched and
honored I am that you waited for
me.
I was starting to think you
wouldn't come back.
Don't be silly! How could I
possibly resist a wonderful
woman like you?
Really?
What is wrong with me? Why do I
feel flustered? I'm supposed to
be the one seducing her!
I waited because I believed in
you. I knew you'd come back to
dance with me.
Believed, in me?
Why would you do that? Why do
you trust me so much?
Huh?
Come on, come on, do it already!
What are you waiting for?!
[Gasps]
One!
Two!
[Screams]
And three.
(All) Mako!
Don't interfere!
[Screams]
We're trapped!
Can't move!
All right, don't just
stand there! Do it!
It can't be. No, please, please
don't tell me you're one of
them!
[Gasps]
You've got yourself to blame.
You must be out of your mind to
put your trust in someone after
you've slow‐danced with him one
time.
Now! [Grunts]
[Screams]
Oh no!
Mako!
[Heavy breathing] Ah!
What's going on?
Usagi, we have to
transform, now!
(Usagi/Chibi‐Usa) Moon Crisis
Make Up!
[Screams]
[Exhales]
What a lovely dream. But not the
one I was looking for.
(Fish's Eye) So no Pegasus, huh?
Then let's get rid of them all
and get out of here.
(Usagi) Oh no you don't!
Huh? Who? Huh?
A woman's intuition is
like telepathy!
We can sense when someone's
toying with the heart of a young
girl blinded by love at first
sight!
How deceitful and
insincere can you be?!
You brats again!
We're the Pretty Guardians.
Who fight for love and for
justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name of the Moon!
We'll punish you!
So what now?
What's your plan?
There's no sign of Pegasus,
so I'm outta here.
You've got to be kidding! Hey,
you've got people to get rid of
here!
She was my beautiful dreamer!
You're the one who butted in, so
deal with it!
Hmph! He never cleans up his
messes.
Fine. Come forth,
my Lemures!
Shufflefuruo, the Sad Playing
Card Master!
Natari‐ hi !
Okay Furuo, take
care of this bunch.
Hey! Come
back here!
Mako!
Okay! Let's play my deal!
(Furuo) Natari‐hi!
Here, let's start with a pair!
[Screams]
[Gasps] They're
sharp as knives!
Sailor Moon!
Behind you!
Huh? [Screams]
Next, two pair!
[Screams]
Three of a kind!
And now, a full house!
Sailor Moon!
[Grunts]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I'm not enjoying this
card game at all!
And now for the kill.
Joker Shower!
Mhm!
[Screams]
Natari! Hi!
[Grunts]
(Makoto) Super Supreme Thunder!
[Screams]
Natari...
Sailor Jupiter!
Way to save the day!
You almost had me fooled, but
you're no Prince Charming.
[Gasps]
Sailor Moon! Chibi Moon! Do your
thing!
Mhm!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Natari! Stage Out!
(Makoto) You know, now that I
think about it, maybe it was
actually the dancing that I fell
in love with.
Twirling round and round to the
music, the crowd parting, all
their eyes on me.
Oh, Mako...
Hey girls! Guess what? They're
having a dance party next week
at the neighboring high school!
You want to go?
(Makoto) I'm in! [Giggling]
[Groans]
Well that's
Mako, for ya.
Guess she's back
to her old self, again.
Mhm!
This time I'm definitely going
to find my Prince Charming! Just
watch!
[Laughing]
(Fish's Eye) Your
boyfriend is wonderful!
(Usagi) Yeah, isn't he? He's
almost too good for me.
(Fish's Eye) You're right, he is
too good for you. I think I'll
take him.
(Usagi) Huh?
(Fish's Eye) Then it's settled.
From now on, Mamo is mine!
(Usagi) No! You
can't have him!
(Fish's Eye) I'll trade you this
piece of cake for him.
(Usagi) Sweet! I mean,
no way!
(Usagi) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS, "Shadow of Evil: The
Trio's Last Chance."
(Usagi) The Moonlight is a
messenger of love.