(USAGI TSUKINO) Naru, why do you
look so worried?
(CHIBI‐USA) It's 'cuz that
handsome guy's hitting on you,
isn't it?
Don't fall for it, he's just
using you as bait to capture
Pegasus!
(USAGI TSUKINO) Everyone knows
you use carrots to lure a horse.
How dare he treat you like a
carrot!... I am Sailor Moon...
...and in the name of the
Moon...
...we'll punish you!
(SAILOR GUARDIANS) Sailor
Moon...
(USAGI TSUKINO) SuperS!
"Catch Pegasus: The Amazon's
Trap"
[eerie chuckles]
(ZIRCONIA) Alright, quiet!...
Quiet down!
Amazon Trio, are you present?
You summoned us, Madame
Zirconia?
I did.
Pegasus has shown himself to
you several times, now, but you
still haven't captured him.
You haven't even been able to
find his hiding place.
[awkward grunts]
(ZIRCONIA) I'm gravely
disappointed in you. All of you.
If I may
interject
here, Madame
Zirconia...?
What is it, Hawk's Eye?
Forgive me for saying so, but I
think you might be
underestimating our carefully
worked‐out strategy.
(ZIRCONIA) Your what?
You see, we've
just been softening
him up.
But now, he's ripe for the
taking, and I can assure you
that Pegasus will be ours in no
time.
Is that right? You're giving me
your word on that?
Absolutely.
Madame.
(HAWK'S EYE) It's your turn
Tiger's Eye. Have you picked out
your next target?
I don't know, I'm up in the air,
but I guess I'm leaning toward
this one.
Hm. Well, she looks pure enough,
but hardly what you'd call a
knockout.
You think you're gonna find
Pegasus hiding in this girl's
dreams? Really?
If I knew for certain
which girl it was, we wouldn't
be in this predicament. [angry
gulp]
Whoahhh, pal.
You trying to drown yourself in
that stuff? What are you so
upset about?
[groan] What do you think? It's
that ridiculous promise you made
back there!... If I fail this
time... she'll be furious!
You and your big mouth! Making
promises that I have to keep!
He's right. You could
have knocked me over with a
feather when I heard you say
that.
I meant it... I have an ace up
my sleeve.
Something I absolutely guarantee
will capture Pegasus.
What?
Ohh, nevermind. Maybe you won't
even need it, Tiger's Eye...
Anyway, you should be going,
shouldn't you?
Hmph!... "Ace up your sleeve,"
yeah, whatever.
[crowd chattering]
(SERVING GIRL) Okay, who had the
chocolate?
Huh... Umino's really late.
[smug grunt]
Ohh, yeah.
Looking fab as always. But
then... it's hard not to when
you're me.
Now, where is she? Where is my
target?
Uh‐huh!... There she is...
[chuckle]
Ugh! Where the heck is he?
Ah! Finally! Huh?
Oh, I... thought
you were somebody
else! Sorry!
No, believe me, I'm the one
who's sorry.
Sorry that I'm not
this lucky somebody else for
whom such a beautiful girl
is sitting here waiting.
Oh, uhh?
[chuckle] This is going
to be so easy...
Sometimes I think
that being so good‐looking
is almost like cheating.
You sweet thing, would
you like to get a cup of
coffee or something?
Ah! There he
is!
Uhh?
'Bout time.
Hi, Naru!...
Here I am!
Coming!
(TIGER'S EYE) What is that? Is
that hideous creature even
human?
Where have you
been, Umino?
[giggle]
Wait‐‐ Come back‐‐
I've been waiting
for you forever.
[scream]
Sorry, Naru, it
took a while
to pick out
this awesome shirt.
(NARU) Well, you're buying the
ice cream.
[gasp]
Did that girl just choose a
pint‐sized, freakish looking,
google‐eyed midget...
... over me?
It's madness! Did that
really just happen?!
No way...!
[spitting drinks and laughing]
[annoyed grunts]
Sounds to me
like the ladykiller's
lost his touch.
[grunt] Shut up, you!
Ohh, scary!
Well, you're in a real slump, no
wonder you're upset.
I'm done with
her.
A girl who can't even appreciate
physical perfection?!
Well, there's no way Pegasus
could be in the dreams of
somebody like that!
You're just saying that
because you failed with
her. Are you sure she's not the
one?
Actually, even if this
girl isn't the one, she
can still be useful.
How exactly?
Yeah, how? Is this
the ace up your sleeve
that you were talking about?
Yup. Wanna see?
Thanks, But no
thanks. I'll pass.
How 'bout you,
Tiger's Eye?
A purple curtain...
So?
Ah!
Huh?
This isn't any
ordianry cage.
Oh, really?
I've always felt that the
biggest obstacle we'd face in
capturing Pegasus...
...would be the fact that he
doesn't even physically exist in
the real world.
But, then it came to me... By
charging anti‐matter with
negative energy...
...I could create a sub‐space
reality cage that would be able
to confine him.
(TIGER'S EYE) So... this way, we
could go right to capturing
Pegasus...
...and skip all that stuff about
finding someone with
beautiful dreams.
But that still
doesn't explain how
we find him.
We lure him
in.
How?
(HAWK'S EYE) You've seen how
Pegasus appears out of nowhere
whenever someone with beautiful
dreams is threatened.
So, we use
a beautiful dreamer
as bait. Any
beautiful dreamer.
I like it... You may have lousy
taste in men, honey, but you'll
be perfect as bait.
(NARU OSAKA) There it is, "How
To Be A Nurse"
Great! Just what I've been
looking for, 'cuz that's what I
wanna be!
A nurse? What a cliché... the
good part about it is, it makes
my job easy.
A girl like that won't be able
to resist a handsome man with a
serious illness. A terminal
illness.
Huh?
So, fate has
thrown us together
again.
It has?... I'm sorry, have we
met somewhere before?
What?! She doesn't remeber me?
There's something wrong with
this little idiot!
Why's he trembling like that?
Maybe he's sick?
I can understand why you don't
remember me.
But, I remember you and
everything about you! Your
voice, your scent, your
lovliness...
I can't get your face out of my
mind!
He is good‐looking... but he's
glowing like he has a fever...!
[groaning]
[gasp]
I'm sorry if I frightened
you... It's just that I'm sick
and I have only three months to
live.
[gasp] Oh I'm so sorry!
Forgive me, it must be very
annoying having to listen to a
complete stranger complaining
about his terminal illness.
That's okay... [sigh]
[coughs and groaning]
Are you alright?!
Should I call
for help?
Bingo. Worked like
a charm... I've
got her now.
There's‐‐ There's nothing
anyone can do...
The saddest part about dying so
young is that I'll never have
known what it's like to be in
love...
Don't you think that's sad?
Oh, yeah... it's tragic.
Would you be
willing to do
one thing for
me?
Uh, what thing?
What do you
mean?
Would you grant me the favor of
being... my girlfriend?
Whaaaaaaaaa‐‐?!
Don't you see what it would
mean to me? You'd be giving me
something to live for in the few
precious days I have left.
(NARU OSAKA) Uh‐But, bu‐... I,
uh...
(USAGI TSUKINO) Whoa! Three
months to live?! That's so
dramatic.
(MINAKO AINO) Yeah, it's like
a soap opera!
But, who is
this man anyway?
I don't know anything about him.
Okay, but you told the guy there
was no way you could be his
girlfriend, right?
Well, not... quite.
What do you
mean? Why not?
I don't know...
Wait, I don't get it Naru. What
about Umino
(NARU OSAKA) I told the guy I
already had a boyfriend, but he
just kept saying that it would
only be for three months.
Wow...
He's dedicating his last
precious days to love... How
romantic!
What do you
know about romance?
Look, Naru, love and pity are
not the same thing.
Yeah, Rei, I think I know the
difference. But I couldn't just
say no right off the bat. I felt
sorry for him.
You're such a kind‐hearted
person, Naru. Not like Usagi.
And w does
that mean?!
(CHIBI‐USA) You know exactly
what that means!
(AMI MIZUNO) Stop it, you two.
I am the
kindest person I
know!
I'm going. See
you later... Bye!
Wait‐‐!
Oh, I think
we must have
made her feel bad.
I guess, we
might have been
too hard on
her.
But, something's fishy about
this man she met. I have a bad
feeling.
I'm gonna go
check on her
to make sure
she's okay.
[gasp] Yeah, maybe we
should all go.
Good idea.
Wait for me!
Luna, I think you
and I better
investigate this further.
I agree.
Three months... What must it
be like knowing that's all the
time you have left?
I want to help him... I really
do...
But how could I ever explain it
to Umino?
(UMINO) Naru!
Umino!
Hey, what'sa matter? Why do you
look so serious?
Actually, Umino, there's
something I need
to tell you...
[crying]
So you see, it's
hard to know what
I should do.
[sobbing] That's what I love
about you, you're such a warm
and caring person!
Huh?
Your heart's telling you to stay
with him, so stay with him!
Don't worry about me! [sobbing]
Umino, wait!
I'll just go to the mountains
and meditate!
Umino...
(USAGI) Don't worry.
[gasp] U‐Usagi!
He's always overreacting
to everything. You
should really know
that by now.
You think Naru
will be alright?
Yeah, she'll be
fine.
So much drama.
Yeah... But Umino's the one I'm
worried about.
Oh, no, it's Umino! He's
drowning his sorrows in
milkshakes...
One, two, three... Whoa, that's
gotta be about fifteen
milkshakes!
Ohh, I'm getting
a tummy‐ache
just thinking about
it! [queasy]
[chuckle] Hello there.
I'm so glad
you agreed to
see me.
Listen, I really think that we
need to talk.
What's wrong? Why the glum look?
Where's that... beautiful
smile?
It's just that, like
I told you before,
I already have a
boyfriend...
So, what about him?
Well, I realize
he means a
lot to me.
[gasp]
I would never wanna hurt him...
You're worrying too
much about things
that don't really
matter.
Right now, it's just you and me
sitting here alone together in
the moonlight.
Think of the joy
we could bring each
other... That's all that
matters.
Huh?
Aaa! Get away!
I'm sorry. But I can't. I just
can't be your girlfriend,
sorry.
Oh, yeah?!... Well, too late,
honey, what you think doesn't
matter now!
Huh?
Did you think I
could actually fall for you?
What kind of fantasy are you
living in?
Who you?
Who, me? Someone who's only
interested in your dreams!
My what?
I've got to warn Usagi and the
others!
One...!
[gasp]
Two...!
[startled yelp]
...And three!
[screaming]
[fainting]
Comfy? Good.
Let's look at your dream.
Ugh, fifteen milkshakes.
Even I think
that's gross.
Do you think
this means it's
over between Naru
and Umino?
Chibi‐Usa, why are
you so obsessed
with this stuff
anyway?
Well, uh...
Hey! We have an emergancy!
Naru's being attaked by the same
creepy blonde guy who attacked
Reika!
Oh, no!
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) Moon
Crisis Make Up!
[screaming in pain]
Ooh!... Ahh!... Look at
that!... Isn't that
extraordinary!... [grunting and
gasping]
No, nothing... No sign of
Pegasus.
And how come a girl like this
has such beautiful dreams?! It
makes no sense!
Hold it right there!
Huh?
Soon you're gonna
wish you only
had three months
to live!
How dare you toy with a girl's
feelings like that!
(CHIBI‐USA) Yeah, and repay her
kindness with evil!
We're the Pretty Guardians...
...Who fight for love and for
justice!
I... am Sailor Moon!
And, I... am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the
name of the
Moon,
... we'll punish you!
I don't think so, not today.
Now, come forth, my most beloved
Lemures... Otedamako, the
Juggler!
Hep, Hep, Hep, Hep, Hep!
Oooh!
Hep! Hep! Hep! Hep! Hep! Hep!
Hep!
[grunts]
[yelp] No! I'm terrible at this!
Here, you take it!
No thanks!... No, you!
[panicked yells]
[screams]
Hep! Hep!
[grunts]
[pained yell]
[gasp]
Hot, hot hot, hot!
Oh no! She's too quick!...
[gasp]
When you are in trouble, just
call my name... I will always
come to you.
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
Heh!
Huh, huh, huh...!
Heh! Thank you
for playing right
into my trap!
Huh?
[wimpering]
What is this?
Some kind of
cage?
Is it meant
for us‐‐?
Oh, no! It's Pegasus he wants!
[chuckle]
No, Pegasus, stay
away! Go back!
Go back!
Heh!
[panicked groans]
No! Pegasus, no‐‐!
Huh?
[relieved giggles]
Huh?!
I was a fool to
think that Hawk's Eye had come
up with a trap that would
capture Pegasus!
I actually believed all
that sub‐space reality nonsense!
What an idiot!
Stupid piece of junk!
As for these little brats, get
rid of them all, Otedamako!
Hep! Hep! Hep!
Hep! Hep!
Hep!... Hep!
Whoa, that's not even funny,
sharp knives are dangerous!
Hip, Hip, Hiiip‐‐!
[swooning]
Huh?
I can never forgive a villian
who would toy with an innocent
young girl's heart!
I don't remember asking you for
your forgiveness! I'll break you
in half you little geek!
I'll break all of you!
If words were deeds, you'd be a
dangerous man.
Do it, Sailor Moon!
Right!
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Whoa! Stage Out!
[grunting]
[gasp] Naru!
[grunt]
[gasp] A Pegasus...!
It vanished. Just what is that
creature?
You're such an idiot, Umino! Of
course, you're gonna get sick
after drinking fifteen
milkshakes!
[nauseous groaning]
But you cared
that much, that's
so sweet.
So... a get
well gift!
[startled yelp and scream]
(CHIBI‐USA) Mamo is so handsome.
(USAGI) Not to mention kind
and gentle and reliable.
(CHIBI‐USA) No wonder he's so
popular with women!
(USAGI) Yeah, they can't keep
away from him.
(CHIBI‐USA) What if a woman came
along who was more mature and
prettier than Usagi?
(USAGI AND CHIBI‐USA) [gasp]
Mamo might fall for her!
(USAGI) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS: "The Perfect Couple:
Usagi and Mamoru's Love."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.