(Usagi)
Whoa, hold on a minute! Who's
that girl with Mamo?
(Chibi‐Usa)
She say she's your love rival!
(Usagi)
My what ?! Does she think
she can steal Mamo from me?
Well, that's just useless,
useless, useless, useless!...
Hey, she's attacking him! No one
gets away with that!
In the name of the Moon...
We'll punish you!
♪
Usagi)
Shadow of Evil: The
Trio's Last Chance
(Tiger's Eye)
Humph! Another scolding...
Doesn't the old witch realize
we're doing our best?&
It's true. She should at least
give us a chance to explain
before yelling at us.
Exactly! We have no idea whose
dreams Pegasus is hiding in, so
obviously, it's going to take
time... But does she sympathize?
No, all we get from her is...
“You worthless incompetents
have failed again ”"
“Good grief, when are you
finally going to capture
Pegasus, you good‐for‐nothing
numbskulls ”"
Right?
Not bad.
(Hawk's Eye)
Thanks, I've been
working on it for a while.
(Tiger's Eye)
Oh, so you've got time for that
but not for any real work!
(Hawk's Eye)
That's a whole
different thing.
Whatta you mean, a whole
different thing?! If you've got
time for one, you've got‐‐
(Fish's Eye)
Cut it out, guys&
‐Hm?
What's wrong, Fish's Eye?
Yeah, why so melancholy?
I'm not. It's just,
what do you think is going to
happen to the three of us if we
keep failing to find Pegasus?
Search me.
I don't know.
Probably nothing that bad.
It's almost like the Madame
doesn't expect us to succeed.
Well, you do
have a point there.
Huh?
[wings flapping]
Oh, it's Zircon.
Our new target, huh?
(Tiger's Eye)
You want to handle this one?...
‐Huh!? It's a guy!?
[big swoon]
He's...gorgeous!!
Hey! What happened?
Weren't you all melancholy
just a minute ago?!
This is a whole different thing.
You really do love the guys,
don't you, Fish's Eye?
Yeah, that may be, but he
still gets dumped a lot.
Only because I
wasn't even trying!
Once I get serious, there's
no person alive I can't win!
Pretty big talk.
Then let's see you get
serious for a change.
Huh! I will, but they gotta
be worth the effort.
[sigh] And this one's definitely
worth the effort.
(Usagi)
Soo cute! Oh my
gosh..! [giggle]
Oooh! And that one!
And that one...
Haaa what a goofy face!
But still cute!
Look at this one over
here! He's cute, too!
Oh, and this one
is cuter! Ha ha ha!
No! This one's cuter! Hee hee!
Wow...
Those fish are very rare.
They're from the Amazon River
in South America.
They're like little
swimming jewels.
They are pretty.
Yeah. I'm tempted to
get some myself.
Oh, boy... they sure
do look tasty.
[groans]
Have you always been into
tropical fish, Mamoru?
Uh‐huh.
I thought it was time I tried
introducing some more exotic
species into my collection.
But don't you think the tank
in your room is already too
crowded?
Hmm... You seem to know a lot
about what's going on in his
room, Usagi.
[embarrassed sigh]
Ahh! What a coupla' love birds!
Hey, that's enough, cut it out!
Stop it, you're embarrassing
me!...
(Minako)
Oh, come on, Usagi!
(Thinking)
Bingo. There he is.
[small grunt]
Why do you keep fish as pets?
They're so boring.
Huh?
Is it because they fill a
yearning left in your heart by
your current girlfriend?
Who're you?
[giggle]
I feel so sorry for
your pet fish.
[gasp]
It's lonely being in a
relationship with a glass wall
between you. [pained gasp]
[gasp]
Are you okay!?
Ow...
(Mamoru)
Looks like you've cut yourself.
[gasp]
[shy sigh]
Can I see your hand?
Oh! Yeah.
[gasp]
(Thinking)
What was it that I just felt?...
Could he be..?
(Usagi)
Ohh, Mamooo???
Usako?
What were you just doing?
Wait! Wait, it's not
what you think!
No makeup, zero sex appeal...
figure isn't bad, I guess, but
still, it's pretty obvious who
wins this contest.
What!?
Sorry, but I'm
taking him from you.
Hey, hey, hey‐‐
What did you just say??!...
Hyaah!
Who are you, anyway?!
Well, let's just say I'm
your love rival, okay?
My rival?!!
Yep. Even though, frankly,
my dear, you're not really
much of a rival.
[low groaning]
(Usagi)
Mamo, what's going on here?!
(Mamoru)
I‐‐I don't know!
What's the matter?
(Usagi)
I demand an explanation!
(Mamoru)
Don't look at me! I'm just
as confused as you are!
[sniff sniff] I
know that smell...
A cat!!?
Calm down, Usako, are
you barking at me!?
[barking]
Wait...
Sorry, something just came up so
I really have to get going, but
I'll see you again soon, okay?
Bye‐bye now!
Who was that?
No idea...
[panting]
(Thinking)
I was so close...
[gasp]
(Thinking)
I sensed a powerful energy...
He definitely could
be Pegasus's host...
And he's really
handsome, too...!
I could...seriously
fall for him...
Curse you, Pegasus, whose
dreams are you hiding in?...
[groan] All this pacing back and
forth is killing my feet...
He keeps popping up everywhere
and yet we're unable to capture
him. It's very annoying.
[distant giggling]
Ah. Hello, girls.
You've finally awakened, I see.
[playful giggling]
I know how you feel, but let's
not smash the orb just yet.
Yes, they're expendable pawns,
but they have their uses.
I know, thank you.
I'm already fully aware that our
queen, Nehalennia, is becoming
quite upset.
Mamo.
“Mamo's ” what they
call you, right?
You again?
So, got a minute?
No, sorry, I'm in
kind of a hurry.
Argh!
[gasp]
[grunt]
[gasp] Come on, why not?
She doesn't have to know.
That's not really
the issue here.
You don't find me attractive?
I didn't say that...
I'm just not interested
in anyone but her.
Why? That doesn't make sense!
What's so special about
a girl like her?
Like I said, I'm in a hurry.
You can't go!
You're...the first one I've
ever been serious about.
Why not?
Fine, just tell me: What's so
great about that Usagi? Why
choose her?
She's full of
dreams, that's why.
Dreams?
♪ Sailor Moon
Oh. There you are... Madame
Zirconia wants to see us...
She seems pretty upset.
[sigh]
What's up with that guy? Did you
already take care of him?
No.
Ah, that might explain it.
Is having dreams...such
an amazing thing?
Huh?
Look around, there are so many
pleasures right in front of
us...
Why would anyone prefer dreams,
when you don't even know if
they'll come true?
Meaning..?
One...!
Argh!
Two...!
Three!
[agonizing screams]
Huh?
What're you doing??
Just as I thought,
no Dream Mirror.
Huh?
Why is it that we don't dream
beautiful dreams, like other
people do?
Huh??...Well, be glad we don't.
Having dreams just makes life
difficult.
[gasp]
Huh? Hey! Where are you going?
Get me off of this thing!
(Zirconia)
You are not worthy!
Nevertheless, Queen Nehalennia
deigns to have words with you.
So listen well.
Queen who?
...Ne‐who‐what‐ia?
Forgive me, madame, but
who is Queen Nehalennia?
She's the great, all‐powerful
ruler of our people...
as well as the most beautiful
being in this universe.
[gasps]
We are ready, your majesty!
Appear and speak to us!
[gasps]
I despise waiting.
And I have no use for
useless servants...
Fail once more and the magic
spell cast upon you will be gone
by the next new moon....
Hurry& You must hurry.
I think she made herself clear.
There can be no more failures.
Just a minute.
Hm?
What did she mean by that stuff
about a magic spell cast upon
us?
[evil laughter]
Excuse me, but what's so funny?
Oh, dear, dear. So you still
haven't realized what you really
are?
[gasp]
Time you learned...
All right, then. See yourselves
as you truly are!
[gasps]
It can't be!!
Wait‐‐ Are you saying...?
... tha what we really are??
Now do you understand?
You are not human...
I merely used magic to
give you a human form.
I see. And that's why we don't
have beautiful dreams?
Huh?
This magic, it will last only
till the coming of the next
new moon...
...But there is one hope.
Pegasus. Find him and capture
him, because only by using the
power of that horn on his head
known as the Golden Crystal
...will you be able
to remain as you are!
There is no other way!
(Fish's Ey)
Waiting for someon?
Huh? Argh!
Not you again...
[giggle] Are you
meeting that girl?
That's right.
Do you enjoy being
with her, Mamo?
Yeah, of course I do.
Ah.
Tell me... what if there were
bad people who were after you?
Huh?
And what if I promised to
protect you from those people...
...and I really meant it...
And all I asked in return was
that you stay with me until the
next new moon...
would you do it?
What're you talking about?
I'm serious! I promise! I
really, really promise! So‐‐
[sad sigh]
I'm not sure I follow.
But being make‐believe lovers in
return for a favor seems pretty
sad, if you ask me.
[embarrassed gasp]
What kind of dream is that?
I see. Dreams again...
I get it now...
It must be nice
having such fine dreams...
Well, big deal!
[gasp]
One...
Huh!?
Two...!
Argh!
And three.
[agonizing scream]
Chibi‐Usa, why don't you be a
good little girl and run on
home now?
Don't want to!
I have a date, so I'm not
asking, I'm telling y‐‐
[Mamoru's screams]
That voice!
(Mamoru)
[agonizing screams]
It's Mamo!
We have to transform!
(Chibi‐Usa / Usagi)
Moon Crisis Make Up!
♪ Sailor Moon...
Sailor Moon... ♪
(Fish's Eye)
Ah yes, The Dream Mirror
that shows... your
beautiful dreams...
Huh.
(Sailor Moon)
Hold it right there!
There are many good‐looking
men in this world.
But you've attacked the
best‐looking of them all, which
means you've got good taste.
Way | good for your own good!
We're the Pretty Guardians...
...who fight for
love and justice!!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name of the Moon...
‐we'll punish you!
So...you two will keep
interfering till the very end.
The end?
Come forth, my Lemures
Tobihaneru, the Trampoline
Acrobat.
Here!
Keep these girls busy
for me, will you?
As you wish!
[gasps]
And now, it's show time!
Huh?
[screams]
Up you go!
[screaming]
Very good!
Now all together! Down we go...
And up we go...!
Fun, eh?
Higher!
That's it!
Feel the burn!
In your thigh muscles!
Now, let's have a
look at your dreams.
[agonizing screams]
[gasp] Pegasus isn't here!
But‐‐ It can't be, I was
sure you were the one..!
No, no, no, no!
[gasp]
[gasps] Mamo!
Chibi Moon!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
♪
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
Stage out!
(Usagi)
[groaning] Oh, Mamo,
you alright?
[delirious groans]
[rainfall]
That weather report
lied! It's pouring!
[gasp] It's that girl...
(Usag)
What's wrong?
Come on, now. You won't
be much of a love rival
looking like that.
♪
(Fish's Eye)
What's your greatest dream?
(Usagi)
Mine? To marry Mamo,
of course. [giggle]
(Fish's Eye)
I envy you and your
beautiful dreams...
...I wish‐‐ I wish I
had dreams, too...
(Usagi)
What's the matter?
(Fish's Eye)
I'm sorry! Please die so I can
make my dreams come true!
(Usagi)
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Mirrors of Dreams: The Amazon's
Last Stage."...
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love...