(USAGI) Don't worry, I'll find a
way to make you better again, I
promise.
(USAGI) And protect the planet
at the same time.
(USAGI) Chibi Moon!
Chibi Moon, can you hear me?
Hang on! I'll get you out of
there, don't you worry!
[grunt] Whoah...
Sailor Moon!
Chibi Moon!
[laughing] Pegasus and his
host... are now in our
possession!
Pegasus and...
...his host?
Chibi Moon... Chibi Moon!
(THE AMAZONESS QUARTET) Always
remember not to forget. A
child's dream is a dream they
should never get.
Always remember not to forget...
(USAGI) Labyrinth of
Mirrors: Chibi Moon Captured
(USAGI) Another fork in the
road...
(MAKOTO) Which way do we go?
That way.
Right.
Stay sharp. I sense a massive
aura of darkness coming from
this direction.
Ahhh! Omph!
Now where am I?
[gasp]
The Stallion Reve...
Pegasus?... [gasp]
Huh?
[gasp]
[gasp] Helios...?
[blushing]
Is that you?
Nice to meet you! Must've been
really terrible, being all
alone in a place like this.
Hang on, I'll get you out of
there.
(QUEEN NEHALENNIA) I can't let
you do that.
[gasp]
[gasps and straining]
So, it was you all along. You
were Pegasus' host.
Who're you?
I am Nehalennia... Queen
Nehalennia, ruler of the Dead
Moon.
[gasp]
Some queen.
Why are you keeping Helios in a
dark place like this?
You can't even imagine the true
depths of darkness.
A child who's walked in light
all your life, you could never
know how I feel.
It all began eons ago...
Back then, there was a kingdom
on the Moon, filled with
light... It was known as Silver
Millennium.
[gasp]
This kingdom flourished under
the rule of a queen named
Serenity.
But there was another queen,
the Queen of Darkness... and she
observed Silver Millennium from
her dark and cold asteroid.
The Queen of Darkness envied the
prosperity of the Moon
Kingdom...
and she yearned to find some way
of making that kingdom her own.
In time, the Queen of Darkness
learned of a mystical stone
possessing unimaginable
powers...
With this stone's power, she
could usurp the Queen of the
Moon's throne... More than
that...
she could eventually rule
the universe!
This stone, the Golden Crystal,
was located in a sacred place on
Earth... where it was protected
by a young man.
[gasp]
The Queen of Darkness
experienced emotions she could
not comprehend.
She found herself desiring not
just the stone... but the young
man as well.
She approached the young man and
proposed that they rule the
universe together, using the
power of the Golden Crystal.
It's thye Golden Crystal that
chooses its owner...
If you possess a beautiful
dream... then you can acquire
this stone... However... if you
do not...
If you do not... then you will
be punished for possessing an
evil heart.
(QUEEN NEHALENNIA) The sacred
flames prevented the Queen of
Darkness from acquiring the
Golden Crystal... What's more...
the Queen of the White Moon
sealed her away in the Darkness
of the New Moon!
But the Queen of Darkness simply
bided her time and awaited her
chance... She knew that if she
had the Golden Crystal...
she could break free of her
prison.
Then, when the solar eclipse
she'd been waiting for
occurred...she unleashed her
minions...
[laughter]
...and succeeded in making that
young man her prisoner!
What happened to you wasn't
Helios's fault! So why don't you
let him go!
You're right. My real grudge is
with those of the White Moon.
And the time for revenge has
come!
[pained screams]
They will all have a taste of my
vengeance, beginning with you!
No matter what you do to me, you
won't get your way‐‐! [pained
scream]
No one who defies me will go
unpunished!
[pained screams and passing out]
Hmph!
Zirconia!
I am here, my queen!
You've done well,
Your majesty is too kind.
But the other people of the
White Moon are still alive out
there. Get rid of them at once.
My queen.
(JUN‐JUN) Man! This totally
sucks!
Yes, it's very disappointing.
Palla‐Palla wants to ride
Pegasus!
She's cut us out of the loop!
It's so unfair!
Mhm!
I say we go tell her off!
Forget it. You shouldn't even be
thinking about defying Queen
Nehalennia.
By the way...
...what is that thing...
...you're making there?
Something to look at stars with.
Something to what?
I thought I'd expand my horizons
a little.
It's done! The peeking Orb!
Well, isn't that odd.
(JUN‐JUN) Hey!
(PALLA‐PALLA) You shouldn't spy!
(CERE‐CERE) I'll tell Queen
Nehalennia.
I can't seem to adjust it right.
Oh, dear.
I get it.
That is a problem.
Let's see. Cloning Orb!
Well, look at that!
Not bad.
But, what if Queen Nehalennia
mistook it for the real one by
mistake? May I?
Open Orb.
(PALLA‐PALLA) Applause!
Applause!
Hush!
[chuckle and grunt]
Oh no, now anybody could just
sneak right in there.
After all the trouble the queen
went through to capture her...
...what if some bad kids came
along and pulled a swap?
Yeah, but of course...
...that would never be us.
Of course not!
(QUEEN NEHALENNIA) There's no
escape for you now.
I may not have a beautiful
dream, but with the power of
Darkness that I now possess...
I'm more than strong enough to
bend the Golden Crystal to my
will.
But first to deal with you
people.
What are all these mirrors for?
(MAKOTO) Someone must be
pretty into themselves.
(REI) Sailor Moon, you coming?
Oh. Yeah, wait up!
Just you wait, little girls...
[grunts]
Go forth! Go forth and destroy
those cursed brats!
Where did everyone go?
[uneasy breath]
That you, Sailor Moon?
Girls?
I seem to have lost them.
How did we all get seperated?
[gasp]
Sailor Jupiter.
Huh?
Behind you.
It's me.
[gasp]
Come on. Don't be afraid.
I'm you, Jupiter.
You're me?
That's right. I'm you... The
real you.
Why am I fighting as a Guardian
in this costume? It isn't really
me, I'm much more feminine than
this.
My dream is a life surrounded by
flowers and sweets. But no one
undertands me...
How am I supposed to become the
girl I wish to be, if all I ever
do it fight?
[chuckle] Look.
Huh?
Gorgeous, right?
[gasp]
Why can't I dress like this in
the real world?
We should just quit.
What do you mean quit?
[chuckle] Quit all this silly
fighting and come join me... in
a wonderful dream.
Do I really have time for all
this nonsense?
My real dream, has always been
to become a doctor, right?
Have I really decided to throw
away my dream?
Throw away.. my dream...?
We both know all the sacrifices
we've had to make fighting for
the people. And what do we get
for it?
Let's ditch this bunch of
ingrates and live for our own
dream.
Of course I'm afraid. There's no
guarantee that we'll win every
battle.
We could even die in the next
one.
Makes me want to run away.
Run away...
(YOUNG SAILOR GUARDIANS)
[laughter]
Huh? [gasp]
You're scared, right? I can
tell.
Who‐‐?
I'm you, Sailor Moon.
You're me...?
That's right. I know all about
you.
You don't want to be here.
...Let's go away and dream, our
own dream together...
Our own dream...?
That's right. Forget everything
else... and dream a wonderful
dream.
(MAMORU) Usako...
[gasp]
Sailor Moon! Help me!
[choked up gasps]
What's worng? Does it hurt
somewhere?
[catching breath]
Can't you tell?
[taken aback]
You know all about me, but you
don't understand the pain I
feel?
Mamo, your pain is my pain.
Usako...
As a child, I didn't have to
worry about anything.
But now, I have friends to share
all my joys and sorrows with.
And I wouldn't have it any other
way. I don't regret who I am
now... Not for a second!
[grunt]
(USAGI) You are not me!
So let's see who you really are!
Moon Tiara Action!
[flinching]
Wretched brat!
(MINAKO) Venus...!
...Love and Beauty Shock!
Mercury...!
...Aqua Rhapsody!
[grunt]
Everyone!
You thought you could trick us
with your spell, huh?
Don't underestimate the Sailor
Guardians!
We haven't forgotten the dreams
of our childhood!
And we never will. But right
now...
...we have a much greater dream
to fulfill!
Dream on! None of you is ever
going to make it out of this
labyrinth alive! I'll see to
that!
(REI) What the...!
(AMI) Is that...?
(USAGI) It's Chibi Moon!
[gasps]
Chibi Moon!...
Wake up, Chibi Moon!
Now he's finally ours!
So pretty!
I get to ride him first!
[chuckle]
‐Hey!
‐No fair!
[grunts]
Whoah! [pained grunts and
groans]
Oh, that's right, Pegasus
doesn't have a physical body.
What're you looking at, huh?
Hey, is he making fun of us?!
In case you haven't noticed, we
captured your host.
Yeah, so you better do as we
say, or else‐‐... Are you even
listening?
Not the most cooperative horse
in the world, is he?
Fine then . Leash Orb!
(VES‐VES) Even you can't get out
of that, Pegasus.
You're going to be our pet,
whether you like it or not.
Huh?
Wow. Pretty horn.
Hey, is that what I think it is?
It must be the Golden Crystal!
Y'think it comes off?
Mmm...
I'm taking it!
‐Hey!
‐No fair!
‐Huh?
[chuckles and arguing]
Ahhh! [grunts]
That was rude.
I am really not liking your
attitude, Pegasus.
Palla‐Palla got a burn!
Let's teach him a lesson.
Go... tighter!
[groggy groan]
Pegasus? Pegasus!
Stop it! What are you doing to
him?!
Hey, we didn't start that fire,
don't go blaming us.
Huh?
Yeah, he's the one who set
himself abalaze, tell him to
stop it.
And soon, or‐‐
‐‐he's going to be a barbecued
horsey.
[gasp]
(JUN‐JUN) Actually, I think
it's too late anyway.
(VES‐VES) Guess we'll just have
to watch him die.
Pegasus! [grunts]
[grunts]
I don't believe it...
She ran into the fire.
[grunts]
Chibi Moon!
Hmmm?
Oh, Pegasus...
I don't get it...
Why would you risk your own life
like that?
What do you mean, "why?" I
didn't even think about it... I
just wanted to save Pegasus.
(ZIRCONIA) Girls!
Uh‐oh!
What have you done, you
insuffereably insolent and
stupid fools?!
Huh?! Ahhh!
[gasp and scream]
Chibi Moon! No!
[screaming and passing out]
No!
[gasps]
Chibi Moon...
Hey, let us out of here, Granny!
Don't worry, Queen Nehalennia
will get us out of here for
sure!
Oh, yes, of course she will.
Right, Jun‐Jun? Hello?
What's wrong Jun‐Jun?
Is something on your mind?
That little one they call Chibi
Moon...
Hmmm?
We're definitely stronger than
she is, but somehow it's like
she's better than us.
Y'know what I mean?
Mm‐hm.
(QUEEN NEHALENNIA) The time has
come to break this loathsome
seal.
Not even the Golden Crystal's
sacred flames can stop me now.
(USAGI) No. The Golden Crystal
embodies the beautiful dreams of
people living on Earth! I won't
let you take away their dreams!
(QUEEN NEHALENNIA) You fool!
Helios, this world, and the
Golden Crystal will all be mine!
(USAGI) Next time on Sailor Moon
SuperS, "The Golden Crystal
Appears: Nehalennia's Magic."
The moonlight is a messanger
of love.