(USAGI TSUKINO) To have to
choose between following your
dream or being with the one you
love...
I could never choose one over
the other!
And, as for that evil creep
trying to take advantage of a
young woman's dilemma‐‐!
Well, anyone who messes with the
red strings of fate has to
answer to me, Sailor Moon!
In the name of the Moon, I'll
punish you!
(SAILOR GUARDIANS) Sailor
Moon...
(USAGI TSUKINO) SuperS!
[eerie laughter]
Tiger's Eye failed,
you say? That's
incredible , I can't
believe it!
Well, he didn't
find Pegasus. I'd
call that a
failure.
And to make it worse,
he didn't even get rid of the
girl with beautiful dreams,
either!
Ooh,Madame Zirconia must be
furious!
[chuckling]
I hope she doesn't punish him
too sever [giggling]
[freaky laughter]
(ZIRCONIA) Alright, Quiet
down!... Quiet!
Amazon Trio, are you present?
Present.
(ZIRCONIA) Capturing Pegasus is
the first step towards world
domination.
We cannot allow this
once‐in‐centuries opportunity
to slip through our fingers!
Now, go!
Find the one in whose beautiful
dremas Pegasus is hiding and
capture him! Do I make myself
clear?
Yes, madame.
(USAGI TSUKINO) "Super
Transformation Once Again:
Pegasus's Power"
(TIGER'S EYE) Oh, please ! You'd
be upset too if everyone was
calling you a failure!
I was doing just fine. I had the
girl wrapped arounf my finger‐‐
[sipping]
And, then, those so called
Sailor Guardians had to come
butting in!
Maybe you shouldn't have let
your personal tastes interfere
with your work...
What does that mean?!
He's got a
point.
Shut up, Fish's
Eye‐‐ What is
that thing?
What, this?
I just found it lying around the
tent. It's a saddle!
When I capture
that flying horse,
I'm going to strap this
on him and ride him!
Ooh, I love it! I've
always wanted to be
a cowboy! I'd look great
in buckskin!
Hey. Check this one out, she's
perfect.
Lemme see,
lemme see!... Oh,
you're right, she's
totally perfect!
[chuckle]
Right.
Hm.You have the worst taste,
both of you.
What are you
so huffy about?
Chill out.
[chuckle]
Well, anyway, it
looks like we've
found our next
target. Right?
Yeah.
(USAGI TSUKINO) So, this is
where it all happned.
(AMI) I'm not really
seeing much in
the way of clues.
(REI HINO) A new enemy,
and this mysterious
Pegasus...
Chibi‐Usa, are you
sure you don't know
anything about any of
this?
[gasp]
Tell no one... Our meeting must
be a secret.
[sigh] No, nothing.
I wonder if I'll ever see him
again...
[gasp]
Chibi‐Usa‐‐! Where are
you going?
[breathless gasps]
[gasp]
[stunned]
Hup, hup...
Hup, hohhh [scream]
[grunt]
[gasps]
It's Reika!
Wait, when did
she get back
from Africa?
You all know
her?
Of course we
know her, she's
Motoki's girlfriend.
Huh‐‐?
Why are we
just standing here?
Let's see if
she needs help!
Mhm!
(AMI MIZUNO) Sorry, Reika, are
we keeping you from practice?
Hm? [chuckle] No, that's
alright.
I couldn't stay
focused today anyway.
My horse definitely made
it clear I was wasting both
of our time.
I just can't concentrate... I
can't get my worries out of my
head.
(USAGI TSUKINO) Why, what is
it? What's worrying
you?
Well, you see... my research has
gone so well that they've asked
me to continue it at a really
prestigious university in Europe
The thing is, if I accept
the offer, it could be almost
ten years before I return to
Japan.
Huh?!
Does Motoki know
about this? Have
you told him?
Yes, I did... But he just smiled
and said, "I'm happy for you"...
That was it.
Since then... I've gone by his
place to talk about it, but I
think he's been avoiding me...
I wonder... if maybe this is his
way of saying he's finally over
me.
[gasp] Hey, I
know, Reika!
Wah! Don't you worry, we'll find
out how Motoki really feels!
[awkward chuckle]
Huh? But I...
I totally know what it's like to
be seperated from the one you
love! It's so painful!
When a friend
of ours has love
problems, we help
her out!
So, just leave everything to us!
Alright.
(USAGI TSUKINO) C'mon, Motoki,
you've got to go see Reika!
She needs you
to help her
make up her
mind!
I appreciate your
concern, but there's
no point in me
seeing her.
I mean, it's her choice.
She has to decide for herself
whether she wants to go to
Europe or not.
Now, if you girls
don't mind, I've gotta
get back to work.
See ya.
Well, that was
rude.
What do you
expect? Nobody likes
being confronted like
that.
Yeah, don't be
a busybody.
Quiet, you!
Are you really suggesting that
the Goddess of Love shouldn't
help her friends with love
problems?!
Yeah! What she
said!
Hmph!
More importantly, girls,
shouldn't we really be
discussing this new enemy of
ours?
Ami! You don't
think what's happening
between Motoki and Reika
is important?
Yeah, what she
said!
Well, sure I
do. Of course...
Do you think it's
possible that Motoki
really has lost interest
in Reika?
Hmmm...
(UNAZUKI FURUHATA) Sorry about
that...
My brother gets so stubborn
sometimes, it's ridiculous.
He'll never let on, but he's
actually taking it really hard.
Duh. Of course!
Nobody could feel good
about being seperated from the
person they love! I mean, come
on!
Usagi... Problems between you
and Mamoru?
Ohhh, where to
begin? ...It's so
sad...
(REI HINO) Don't listen to her.
She's just upset because
she doesn't know where Mamoru's
been since yesterday afternoon.
Wait. How do
you know about
that?
'Cuz she talked
my ear off on the
phone last night.
Oh. Mine, too.
Yep.
Same here! So
she actually called
every one of us
last night?
Uhh...
[sheepish giggle]
(REI HINO) I mean, seriously.
Someone who's freaking out
because she hasn't seen her
boyfriend in half a day...
...has no right to say she
understands how Motoki feels!
Well, I, uh...
I was lonely,
okay? [bawling]
[groans]
(CHIBI‐USA) Here you go!
Do you like
horses Chibi‐Usa?
Mm‐hm!
[chuckle] You've got such a big
face!
And, also, you've got such
pretty eyes.
(REIKA NISHIMURA) They ae pretty
aren't they? So clear and
pure...
You can't ever lie or pretend to
an animal... They can look
inside your heart and see what's
really there.
Mmm.
Reika? Ever seen a horse with
wings and a horn on its head‐‐?
Like that!
Sounds like a creature out of a
dream world.
A dream world... Yeah.
It would have to be a beautiful
dream, though, for a creature
like that to be living in it.
You know, I wouldn't be a bit
surprised if you'd met a
creature like that, Chibi‐Usa...
Seems to me you're practically
bursting with dreams.
Yeah... But the dreams I have
aren't all that "beautiful"...
I'm sure you must have really
beautiful dreams, Reika.
Ohh, I don't know about that...
It seems like my dream is just
making the people who love me
feel sad and lonely...
That doesn't sound very
"beautiful" , does it?
It's not good enough, Minako. We
have to go to Crown again
tomorrow and find out how Motoki
really feels.
Luna, what do
you think will
happen with Reika
and Motoki?
Well, ten years is
a long time. I'm afraid
this might finally be the
end of things for them.
(USAGI TSUKINO) What? Mamo? No,
he hasn't called! I haven't
heard a word!
[sigh] They do say that
long‐distance relationships are
hard to maintain...
I guess, when you're far apart
from someone, your heart can
grow distant, too, maybe.
Awww Chibi‐Usa...
Right! See you tomorrow.
Huh...? Minako? That you, again?
[scream] Mamo! Where are you?
It's been ages. What have you
been doing? Why haven't you
called, huh?!
I'm at a seminar I have to
attend for my major. And I've
been trying to tell you since
last night...
But every time I call, the
line's busy! Do you have to make
such long phone calls?
[sheepish chuckle]
(MAMORU) Anyway, have you had a
chance to talk with the others?
Huh?
About our new enemy. Have you
forgotten?
Oh, right! About our new enemy,
totally!
We are carefully formulating an
appropriate plan of action!
Correct! Uh huh! First thing
tomorrow! Right!
I will eagerly be awaiting your
return! [heavy sigh]
[happy sigh] Ohh, Mamo! [giggle]
On the other hand, Luna, no
matter hoe far apart I am from
Mommy and Daddy, I still love
them and I always will.
And I know they love me, too.
That's why they sent me here for
my training.
That's right, you can't give up
just because you're far apart.
Where's the hope and dream in
that?
Hup, hup, Hohhh!
[gasp]
Easy, now... It's okay, it
wasn't your fault.
[gasp]
It's amazing... For a minute, I
thought a goddess had come to
Earth on horseback.
[taken aback]
(CHIBI‐USA) Let's go check on
Reika and see how she's handling
things.
[gasp]
Well, I guess she's handling
things pretty darn well.
Ummm...
I can see
you take your
training very
seriously.
Yes, but it's
no use.
Seems the harder
I try... the less
I can keep my
mind on it.
I might be
able to help,
if you'll permit
me.
Wha‐‐?
You see, I can tell. Behind
those levely eyes, I see the
anguish of someone facing a
difficult dilemma.
[gasp]
[chuckle] Women just can't
resist a senstive, soulful man
who's willing to listen to their
problems...
Her heart is already mine.
Oh... I wish
I could hear what
they were saying!
Stop it Chibi‐Usa,
really ... Spying's not
polite.
But Luna... how will I know
what's going on?
Ohh, when it comes
to things like this, you
and Usagi are so alike!
So. Europe, huh?
I don't know
what to do.
Is it right to persue your
dream if it means having to
leave the people you really care
about?
Tell me more.
[gasp]
What is this dream that you
cherish so much that you cling
to it even when it brings you
pain?
[uneasy gasp]
Please... Show me this dream of
yours.
Huh? No!
[chuckling]
[heavy breathing]
[startled groan and grunt]
[chuckle]
Careful now... I wouldn't want
any harm to come to such a
beautiful dreamer.
What‐‐ What do you want?
Hyaah!
[stunned gasp]
One..!
[scared gasps]
Two..!
Three!
[scared groans]
[laughing]
[gasp]
Hurry, Chibi‐Usa!
Transform!
Mhm!
Moon Prism Power Make Up!
[trembling]
(CHIBI‐USA) Hold it right there!
Hm?
I don't care how handsome you
are, you're a creep to take
advantage of a young woman with
love problems!
You know who I am... The pretty
Guardian Trainee who fights for
love and justice!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
In the name of the future
Moon... I will punish you!
Oh no, it's that little bumpkin
from the other day. Yecch!
Come forth, my Lemures.
Kyokubadanko,
the Beast Tamer.
Have fun with her.
Danko dandan!
Hyaaaah!
[dodging grunts]
[screams]
Stop that!
[chuckling]
[frightened gasp]
Let's have a
look at that beautiful
dream of yours.
[gasp] What are you doing? Stop
it, stop it! Please!
Oooh!... Aaah!... Lovely!
[groan]
[sigh] Ahh, she's not
the one, either. Pegasus
wasn't in there.
Kyokubadanko!
Danko dandan?
Get rid of this one
so Pegasus never tries
to hide in her beautiful
dream.
Actually, why don't
you get rid of both
of them?
(USAGI TSUKINO) Oh no you don't!
Sailor Moon!
Thank goodness!
At your service! Whever evil
lurks in the world, I'll be
there at a moment's notice!
I'm the Pretty Guardian... who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor moon!
And now, in the name of the
Moon... I'll punish you!
Good grief... Now
it's a whole
crowd of bumpkins!
Crowd? What do you mean? What
the‐‐? Who, huh... guys?
Surprise. You kept
us waiting around
forever at Crown...
...So, we figured
we'd probably find
you here.
Yeah, plus we
wanted to make
sure that Reika
was doing okay.
I despise such girlish
chatter...Especially when
it means you're all ignoring
me!... Danko!
Dandaan! Let me give you a warm
welcome!... Hyah!
[dodging yells]
That's not being very friendly.
Show some appreciation! Dandan!
How about this instead!...
Burning... Mandala!
Alright, fine, we'll skpip the
pleasantries!
[alarmed gasps]
Rings of Fire!
[dodging yells]
[cackling]... Keep it up! Make
them do tricks, Danko, make them
dance or something!
Dandaaan! You too,
squirt! Put on
your dancing shoes!
[scream and grunts]
The can‐can!... Go!... Dance!
[frantically dancing and
dodging]
Faster, faster!... Kick those
legs!... Higher!... Faster!
Passe!... Lemongrab!...
Ominelle! Manana!... Again!
[cackling]
[yelp]... What do I do?!
Help us, Pegasus!... Please...!
[gasp]
Huh?
He's come back...!
[gasps]
[determined grunt]
[charging up efforts]
Stage Out!
I'll make you
Pay! Next time... [grunt]
Rekia!
[gasps]
Is that‐‐?
The one Usagi
told us about‐‐?
Pegasus...
[surprised gasps]
Huh?
Pegasus...
(USAGI TSUKINO) Oh, come on,
Motoki! Stop avoiding her!
Yeah, c'mon, you've gotta
at least see Reika and tell
her how you really feel.
Sorry, I can't.
Okay. Suit yourself,
but can't you
at least eplain
why you won't?
Otherwise, you know
these girls are
never gonna leave
you alone.
[sigh]
It's cause this is Reika's
dream.
So, I promised myself I'd keep
away from her 'til she'd made up
her own mind about it.
I don't want her to abandon her
dream just because she's worried
about how I might feel.
The fact is, I can wait ten
years for her. I'll wait as long
as she wants.
(UNAZUKI FURUHATA) Well, you
can't ask for more than that,
can you?
You heard all
that, right?
[gas] Rei‐‐Reika!
I was‐‐ I was beginning to get
the feeling that maybe you
didn't love me anymore...
That you thought I was, well,
that I was being selfish...
What? Reika, don't be silly!
Why would you
even think that?!
I will always
love you.
[gasp]
Go to Europe... Go and do your
best if that's what you really
want.
[sigh] Motoki...
My brother, what
a guy! [giggle]
Way to go,
Motoki!
[giggles and cheers]
(USAGI TSUKINO) And don't worry,
I'll comfort you when you get
lonely.
(REI HINO) Yeah... he's not
gonna be that desperate...
(USAGI TSUKINO) Hey! That's
rude!
(CHIBI‐USA) I knew it... As long
as they love and believe in each
other, things will work out.
No matter how far you stretch
them, the red strings of fate
that bind them together can
never be broken!
(USAGI TSUKINO) Chibi‐Usa! You
ate my lemon pie again, didn't
you!
(CHIBI‐USA) I did not! It wasn't
even yours. Mommy Ikuko made it
for me!
(USAGI TSUKINO) Grrrr! I can't
believe it! Mom favors you so
much!
(CHIBI‐USA) Yeah, she's a nice
mom... Unlike some other moms I
know.
(USAGI TSUKINO) What's that
supposed to mean?!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Protect Mom's Dream: Double
Moon's New Attack."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.