(Chibi‐Usa)
Whoa! Usagi, what's
with the outfit?
This is the latest fashion!
For a thief spying on someone,
maybe...
You dummy! It's so I can protect
Mamo!
Hey, you! Weirdo! Keep your
hands off of my Mamo, or else...
In the name of the Moon,
...we'll punish you!
♪
Protect Mamoru: Ninja Usagi's
Jealousy
So, the problem here is this
quadratic function.
Oh, I see So, I guess I
should've taken into account the
spatial relations between the
vectors, then.
giggle
Wow, You're catching on pretty
quickly, Ami.
Now, for this one, you can apply
the previous problem to solve
it.
[angry grunt]
(Ami)
Oh, you're right!
That's helpful.
(Mamoru)
Yep, you got it!
[laughter]
Don't sit so
close together!
Come on. Seriously?!
Usagi, you know that he's just
helping her out by tutoring her.
I don't care. I don't want him
looking at other women!
Such a baby.
Yeah, soooo?! Got a problem
with that?
[angry grunts]
Your love for each other has
been burning so long, no
one's gonna mess that up!
Speaking of burning, do
you guys smell that...?
[gasp]
Ahhh! It's a fire!
What!? Fire! Oh no!
Get the fire extinguisher!
Everyone, calm down!
Hey! I found one!
Whoa!
[screaming]
[coughing]
Well, sounds like the smoke
Diana saw was from the fish
being cooked downstairs...
I'm sorry...
No, it's not your fault. Usagi's
silly overreacting made us all
panic, too.
Excuse me!?
‐Usagi!
[groan]
What are you gonna do now,
Mamoru? You can't live here
while it's like this.
Who knows. I have a huge paper
due tomorrow and I'm behind...
I'm gonna have to figure
something out pretty fast.
If that's the case, stay at
my place. It's quiet there.
Whaaaaaaaaat!?
No, no, no, no, no! He's
staying at my place!
How do you plan on explaining
Mamo to mommy and daddy?
[grimace]
Don't you worry, leave it all
to me! I volunteer to go with
them and make sure nothing funny
happens between Master Mamoru
and Master Rei.
I can't unsee that...
Noooo! He can't go!
(Madame Zirconia)
You must hurry!
Our goal of world domination
rests on being able to locate
Pegasus!
With all due respect,
Madame Zirconia,
Our abilities are already far
superior to that of the humans.
(Fish's Eye)
I'm sure conquering the world
would be easy even without
finding Pegasus.
Actually, you've never told
us what Pegasus really is.
All you three need to worry
about is following my orders!
So instead of wasting precious
time making pointless comments,
go find Pegasus' host!
‐Yes, Madame.
Ugh, it's not like we're just
some henchmen running errands.
What's the harm in telling us?
I get the feeling Madame
Zirconia is more interested in
Pegasus than world domination.
What are you even
doing over there?
Clairvoyance.
Since when have you
been clairvoyant?
Be quiet.
See? Not bad, huh?
Ah!
Oh, wow!
Seems I should change my
tactics. Time for a more
traditional approach.
(Rei's Grandpa)
I'm so sorry for the
trouble my Rei caused you.
Please forgive her.
It's fine. It was no
trouble at all, sir.
No, no. After what happened you
can stay a whole year, or even
two if you'd like to.
Dontcha think you're
kind of overdoing
it, grandpa?
(Grandpa)
This one looks like a keeper...
Don't let him get away!
Grandpa!
Hiwaka Shrine has a very long
history, so it's a shame that I
don't have an heir.
If only darling Rei would take a
husband soon, then I would have
a successor.
You seem like a
perfect candidate!
I've seen enough! I'm taking
Mamo back to my place!
Hey! Let go of me!
Stop it, Usagi!
In all the time that I've spent
working at training at this
shrine, my master has never
even once asked me to
become Rei's husband!
Well, yeah, that's
because you're Yuichiro.
[freaking out]
That wasn't very
nice, Usagi.
Even if Mamoru and Rei used to
date before, it doesn't mean‐‐
ARGH! Dated!?
Ahhhhh!!
Ami...
Did they really
used to date?
Yeah, but that
was ages ago!
All those feelings are
long gone by now!
Right! She's still looking for a
boyfriend and just wants to find
the right person!
She's still... looking...
for one...?
[freaking out]
Ahhh!
I guess that
didn't help.
Ooh, what a quiet room. You
should be able to get lots of
work done, Master Mamoru.
Diana, I really wish you'd stop
calling me "Master Mamoru."
Just "Mamo" is fine.
No way! It wouldn't be right
to address our future king
so casually.
Now, because you need to focus
on your studies, I, Diana, will
make sure that no one is able
to enter this room...
Where are you going!?
Hm?
I'm gonna take a bath.
Wanna join me?
Arghhh!
I wish grandpa wasn't in such
a rush to marry me off.
I'm still young and have
a lot to experience!
My career, living life, and
finding love of course!
[shouting]
[gasp] Wow!
What's wrong!? Are
you okay, Rei!?
[gasp]
Huh? What's going
on here?
[shouting]
What did I do?
You idiot! Why didn't you tell
me he was using the bath next
when we passed in the hall!?
Wait! Rei!
[groan]
Ugh, are you enjoying
your bath...
...Chiba?
Hm?
[running]
Ugh! They're all so stupid!
(Usagi)
Who are you calling
stupid...?
Wha? Who's there?
Ugh, it's so crammed
in there....
(Rei)
Usagi!?
What are you
even doing here?
I've been waiting for you for 4
hours! Now be a good girl and
tell me where Mamo is.
Hmph! He's in the bath
right now. He's all yours.
Bath, huh?
Wait a sec... you didn't
peek, did you?
[gasp]
Why are you turning
all red, huh!?
I didn't do it on purpose!
You saw it, didn't you!
It was from behind.
So you saw his butt, then!
Hey look! It was his fault
for letting me see!
How could you, Rei!?
(Rei)
I told you, it
was his fault!
(Usagi)
But you were the
one who looked!
(Rei)
I couldn't look away!
(Usagi)
Then why didn't you
close your eyes!?
[blowing]
If Rei used to date that
guy, then that means...
No! No impure thoughts!
So, you said your name
was Kumada, right?
Sorry to make you
stoke the fire for me.
This is an old and venerable
shrine. So the bath is also
retro.
Yeah, that's great.
But the water's
a little too hot.
Oh? Is that so?
Huh! [blowing]
Heh heh! [blowing]
Ha! [blowing]
[blowing]
(Mamoru)
[screams] Hot!
[sigh]
Huh?
Pegasus!
Hey, I was wondering, why do
people get jealous when they
fall in love.
I always hear Usagi telling Mamo
not to look at other girls.
If she really trusted him
why would she even care?
Perhaps it's because you should
want the one you love to only
have eyes for you.
That sounds lame.
I don't want that.
I trust the one I
love with all my heart.
Yes, trusting and waiting can be
a way to express your love, too.
Yeah! Of course!
Whoaaa!
♪Sailor Moon
[typing]
Ah, I guess I didn't get
much done after all.
There's still lots of time.
Don't give up, Master Mamoru.
Thanks.
I hardly slept last night.
[stretch]
(Usagi)
Why did you hardly sleep
last night, Rei?
Huh?
I left quietly yesterday, but
today I'm not leaving without
Mamo!
Go and get him then.
You're totally delusional if
you think I still have any
interest in him.
How dare you insult
my darling Mamo!
I never insulted him!
Can you please keep
it down out here!?
[groans]
Honestly! You're going to make
Master Mamoru fail his class.
Foiled again! But Mamo won't be
trapped here much longer!
I'll return after breakfast!
She's so annoying!
Yuichiro! Get rid of that ninja!
Oh, come on! Where are you?
Heyyyy!!!
AHHH!!!
M‐m‐master!
So, you're still
alive I see.
You're such
a weakling!
Yes! I, Yuichiro, am nothing
but a foolish weakling!
Be it day or night, I
see only one woman! My
heart feels only for her!
I'm ashamed I still feel this
way despite all of my rigorous
training!
Aha! So, you've
finally come to realize.
Realize what?
You true training begins once
you've severed yourself from
worldly desires!
Are you ready to
follow in my steps?
Yes!
This training
won't be easy.
Yes! Please show me
the way, Master!
Hey lady! Wanna
go out with me?
[gritting teeth]
What are we doing?
Now, you try it.
A young man who only goes after
one woman is no man at all!
[gasp]
Now that you mention it...
They're beautiful!
That's right. Aim
big, my boy.
Yoo‐hoo! Young
ladies!
Miss, excuse me, do you
have... some free time!?
[screaming]
How about you, miss?
Pathetic...
(Tiger's Eye Thinking)
Found her... my next target..
Lovely... A pure and beautiful
young lady... with wonderful
dreams!
It'd be a waste to
simply attack her.
I think I'll try
to win her heart first.
I got you now!
Darn! I thought
it was Usagi.
Oh, I didn't see you there.
Uh... oh!
Ahem...
I have to admit, I was so
smitten by your mysterious eyes,
that my legs just gave way.
Where are you hiding, Usagi?
Here!? Or here!?
Does she not even notice that
I'm here? No one gets away
with ignoring me!
You can't hide from
me forever! I gotcha!
Huh!?
[gasp]
[frightened gasp]
One!
Two!
[frightened gasp]
...And three!
[screaming]
[chuckle] Now, let's have a look
at your beautiful dream...
Ninja... Ninja eye...
sneaky ninja!
Ugh, stop it,
already!
No! I have to protect my beloved
Mamo from Rei's evil hands!
[out of breath]
I wouldn't be surprised
if he dumped you for
being so stubborn.
Here, up you go.
If you really love him, trusting
and waiting can be a way to
express your love, too.
Did you get that out of
a book or something?
[Rei screaming]
‐Huh?
[screaming]
[gasps]
(Usagi & Chibi‐Usa)
Moon Crisis Make Up!
♪
[giggling]
Oh, what a wonderful dream!
Darn! No sign of Pegasus.
Just a pure heart that
dreams of the future!
But I can't have you becoming a
host for Pegasus later...
So, disappear...
(Usagi)
Hold it right there!
How dare you terrorize an
innocent girl who's looking
forward to finding her true
love!
You're an evil man who ruins
people's bright futures
filled with hopes and dreams!
Where are you even
learning this stuff!?
Anyway, we are the
Pretty Guardians!
...who fight for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi‐Moon!
In the name of the moon,
we'll punish you!
Huh, the usual
pains in my neck.
Come forth, my Lemures,
Mizugeiko, the water Geisha.
Aaah!
Aiya!
Just brilliant! Why don't you
help them keep a cool head
with your water skills.
Aiya!
Huh?
[screaming]
Yuck! What is this?
What the heck?
This isn't water!
Ah! Mamo!
Usako... was that you?
(Diana)
Master Mamoru...
You have to keep at it or
you won't finish in time!
Yeah, you're right.
I'll keep going.
water at my whim on
the right side!
...and also on my left!
[frightened]
Aiiiiya!
The Little Rainmaker's
Rainbow Bridge!
[gasps]
Kia!
Huh!?
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[screaming]
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Hiya!
Aiya!
[gasp]
Please, Pegasus, protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
(Sailor Venus / Sailor Jupiter)
Sailor Moon, do your thing!
Okay!
[attack yell]
♪
Moon Gorgeous Mediation!
Stage Out...!
[angry grunt]
[sigh]
You okay?
Sailor Moon!
(Usagi)
How could you! You didn't come
help me when I called for you!
Yeah, I messed up, sorry!
I am so ashamed of
myself, Rei! I gave into
the devil's temptation!
I don't even know what you're
talking about Yuichiro.
[gasp] He's handsome!
I, Yuichiro Kumada, will never,
ever try to hit on other women
again!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
(Fish's Eye)
Do you like young, pretty boys?
(Usagi)
Huh? Well, I guess I
don't hate them...
(Fish's Eye)
Not too young, not
too old, either!
...I just love the
androgynous look!
(Usagi)
Right? It's that slightly
"memanine" quality.
(Fish's Eye)
Ooo! He's pretty cute!
Gotta go! Ta‐ta!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS:
"Forest of Illusion: A Beautiful
Fairy's Invitation."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.