[grunting]
[gasping]
Mamo!
What's the matter?
Is your chest hurting
again?
I've been getting
these sharp pains
ever since the spider
webs showed up.
Guys!
[gasping]
Look, the sun..!
It's going dark!
Is it a solar
eclipse?
Can't be... The
next solar eclipse
shouldn't happen
for a long time.
That big event they
were talking about...
could this be it?
The Dead Moon... the
magic of the New
Moon...
Is the world being
covered in darkness
by the New Moon,
like Pegasus
said?
Okay, we can't let
the enemy have their
way any longer!
I agree.
There's no way
we're just gonna
stand by and
do nothing!
All right, girls,
let's go!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Pegasus!
People of the White
Moon...
You must not face the
Dead Moon just yet.
Huh?
The Source of
Darkness: Dead Moon
Circus
[gasping]
Pegasus!
Hang on, what did you
mean when you said we
shouldn't face the
Dead Moon yet?
Yeah, what exactly
are you saying? Are
you telling us you
don't think we're
strong enough to take
on the Dead Moon?
They cannot be
defeated by brute
force.
The Dead Moon are
monsters born of the
remnants of dreams
discarded by people
who forgot what it
means to dream.
As long as there are
discarded dreams...
... the Dead Moon
will continue to
exist.
Pegasus...just who
are you?
I am Helios, priest
of Elysion... I watch
over the dreams of
the people of Earth.
Elysion?
Pegasus...
Elysion kept the Dead
Moon sealed away
using the power of
people's beautiful
dreams... However,
that seal has
weakened, allowing
them to reawaken.
Including Nehalennia,
Queen of the Dead
Moon!
[cackling]
Now Nehalennia is
stretching out her
evil hands towards
Earth... The only way
to seal her away
again is to activate
the power of the
Golden Crystal.
The Golden Crystal?
This horn of mine is
the Golden Crystal.
It gives off sacred
energy... It is the
one thing that can
seal the Dead Moon
back into the
darkness again.
The Golden Crystal is
said to possess the
power capable of
destroying even stars
and planets.
So that's it. That
explains why the Dead
Moon has been
relentlessly
searching for you.
Yeah, it's because
they want to get
their hands on your
Golden Crystal,
right?
The answer's
simple, then! All you
have to do is use
that Golden Crystal
thingie on your head
to beat the Dead Moon!
That's not how it
works...
[lightly gasping]
See, Pegasus isn't
able to activate
the Golden Crystal
himself... He needs
to find the person who
can release its energy.
Chibi Moon, how
did you‐‐
‐‐know all this?
Pegasus has been
searching for that
person all this time.
But whoever it is,
he hasn't been able
to find them anywhere.
So you knew all
along? Chibi Moon,
why didn't you tell
us about any
of this sooner?!
I asked her not to.
Knowledge of the
Golden Crystal is
something that is
passed on only to the
priest of Elysion...
However, I defied
this code and
revealed its power
and secrets to you.
[gasping]
That's because I
believed that you
were the one who
could activate the
Golden Crystal.
When I was cast into
darkness... it was
none other than you
who shined a
light on me.
But now... we're
running out of time.
[gasping]
Pegasus!
[struggling]
Tuxedo Mask!
Please... Find the
one who can release
the power of the
Golden Crystal.
Pegasus‐‐!
Pegasus.
Please...
Pegasus!
[lightly gasping]
I see that Helios's
soul is communicating
with someone again.
[grunting]
Even in his pathetic
condition, he mocks me.
Although only a shell
of himself, he still
refuses to obey me!
The impudence!
[struggling]
So in order to defeat
the Dead Moon, we're
going to need
the power of this
Golden Crystal?
[struggling]
As strange as it all
sounds, Pegasus is
telling the truth,
I know it.
How, Mamo?
The voice of Pegasus,
I've heard it, too.
What did he say?
Prince Endymion...
your body has become
attuned to Earth,
your Guardian Planet.
Attuned?
These webs eating
away at the Earth are
also eating
away at my body.
If only I was the
person who was able
to release the power
of the Golden
Crystal...
It isn't your
fault.
Diana's right. So what
if we don't have the
Golden Crystal?
Yeah, as long as
we put our powers
together,
we can totally
handle anything.
Don't worry, we
won't let the Dead
Moon Circus have
their way any longer.
Thanks, guys!
Well, come on,
everyone!
Let's go beat Queen
what's‐her‐name!
Right!
Usagi‐‐
Mm.
Let's give them
a minute...
Oh, Mamo...
I'm sorry that, in
a time of crisis,
I'm making you face
the danger alone.
[sniffling]
It's okay, Mamo,
your pain is my pain.
Usako...
Don't worry, I'll
find a way to make
you better again,
I promise.
And protect the
planet at the same
time.
I should go now...
She and Chibi‐Usa
have grown so
strong‐‐
[grunting]
Master Mamoru!
Mamoru!
Hang in there!
[struggling]
[laughing]
[gasping]
What's all this?!
[laughing]
Welcome one, welcome
all! Welcome,
welcome, one and all!
Welcome to the Dead
Moon Circus!
[panicking]
What the hell
is this?!
Dreams dreamed at
night are fleeting,
but our nightmares
are in business 24/7.
Come on, check
them out, they're
the best!
You'll never stop
laughing.
You'll laugh so
much, you might
just‐‐
‐‐become a jackass!
But don't blame us!
[screaming]
Who are you people,
anyway?!
[blowing smoke]
Ah! [coughing]
Will you cut it
out?!!
Whoa.
Guess it never hurts
to ask.
[gasping]
Hey, everyone! Look!
They've cleared a
path straight to the
circus tent.
It looks like they
want to settle this
once and for all, too.
Exactly!
[laughing]
You guys again!
Welcome to the Dead
Moon Circus!
Yeah, Sailor
Guardians! Welcome,
welcome, one and all!
Oh. well, how could
we refuse such a nice
invitation?
Moon Crisis Make Up!
Mars Crystal Power
Make Up!
Jupiter Crystal Power
Mercury Crystal Power
Make Up!
Venus Crystal Power
How dare you turn
our beloved Juban
District into a
jungle of messy
spider webs!
What's more, my
Mamo is in agony
because of you, and
I cannot forgive you
for that!
We are the Sailor
Guardians who fight for
love and for justice!
In the name
of the moon...
...we'll punish
you!
We'll be waiting in
the center ring.
We've got some
special seats there,
reserved just for
you.
Yeah! We'll see you
all there. That is,
if you manage to get
inside the tent in
one piece.
Wait! Come back
here you‐‐
[laughing]
[grunting]
Mars Flame Sniper!
[yelling]
Let's go.
[laughing]
[grunting]
[groaning]
Uh‐oh! They're
pretty strong...
Actually, it's more
like those Lemures
are too weak.
At this rate
they'll blast
through the center
ring and right into
our dressing room.
Yeah, whose brilliant
idea was it to lure
the Sailor Guardians
into the circus,
anyway?
[pointing blame in unison]
Amazoness Quartet...
That voice‐‐!
It's Queen
Nehalennia!
Are you here to give
us a new toy?
Palla‐Palla would
really like some
stronger magic,
and a pony.
Yeah, give us
something powerful so
we can destroy those
Sailor Guardians
with one blow!
Calm down, now.
For you, my darling
children, I do have
some special powers
in mind, now that you
mention it.
Really?
You are so generous,
Queen Nehalennia!
Unlike that stingy
squid‐face, Granny
Zirconia.
The Amazon Stones
that I gave you, take
them out now.
Now, go forth and use
these powers I have
given you to destroy
those of the White
Moon once and for
all!
That Queen Nehalennia
of theirs has got to be
hiding in
here somewhere.
[gasping]
Well, they're very
accommodating,
aren't they?
Chibi Moon, there's
something I wanna ask
you, if you
don't mind.
Seriously, Mercury,
this kid?!
What could she
know that you don't
already know?
Why, you‐‐
What I meant was...
Seeing Chibi Moon
with Pegasus made me
think of something.
It made me remember
that when I was a
little girl, I
thought I saw a white
horse with wings,
too.
You too, Mercury?
Come to think of it,
I did, too.
I dreamt of a white
Pegasus.
A memory from a past
life, maybe?
No... I think It was
a dream.
Yeah, a dream.
The kind of dream
everyone's had as a
child.
Yeah, well, that's
great, but my Pegasus
isn't a dream.
Uh!
Pegasus and I have
shared our worries
and doubts with each
other...We've
laughed together.
It was fun...
I've been so happy
that we're friends.
I want to help
Pegasus...more
than anything!
Chibi Moon...
It's obvious you
really love Pegasus,
don't you?
I'd forgotten what
those feelings were
like...
Years later I
convinced myself that
Pegasus was
just a fairy tale.
I guess I decided to
bury those feelings
and follow my
own dreams.
But if you treasure
the feelings you have
now and hang on tight
to them, then maybe
Pegasus will stay
with you forever.
Hmm.
Thank you. All
of you!
Where are we?
[elephant trumpeting]
[laughing]
[grunting]
Weeeee!
Thank you for your
patience!
We proudly present
the stars of the Dead
Moon Circus...
...the Amazoness
Quartet! Showtime,
girls.
Batter up!
[flinching]
[grunting]
Meant to say. If you
drop 'em they just
might explode.
Are you all right?
Jupiter‐‐!
[giggling]
Here you go!
[gasping]
Ew, it stinks!
Gross!
[yelling]
Rolling Orb!
Stop following me!
Ahhhhh!
They're so much
more powerful than
they were before!
What is going on??
This is nothing!
[winding up]
Natto Orb!
Look out!
[grunting]
What is this stuff?!
Oh, no!!
Stay away! Don't
touch us or you'll
get stuck, too!
Well, that was easy.
So, whatta you think?
Should we go ahead
and get rid of them?
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's do it!
[gasping]
Noooooooo!
The Crystal
Carillon!
Helios's body...
it's resonating!
Does this mean that
the host of Pegasus
is somewhere nearby?
Who is it? Who hides
the Golden Mirror?!
Is that girl the one?
Are you telling me to
summon you, Pegasus?
Chibi Moon!
Huh!
Twinkle Yell!
[gasping]
[struggling]
[falling]
Moon Gorgeous
Meditation!
[screaming]
[cackling]
[gasping]
Okay, who's this
now?
I am Zirconia, troop
leader of the Dead
Moon.
I know the truth.
That Pegasus is just
an illusion. The real
Pegasus can survive
in the human world
only by residing in
someone's beautiful
dream.
That being so, we
simply need to
capture his host.
Huh?
[screaming]
Ahhh!
Chibi Moon‐‐!!
[screaming]
[horse whinnying]
Ah...At last I've
found you...
Pegasus' host.
[gasping]
So that's the
Golden Mirror..!
Cool!
N‐‐ No!
Now!
[gasping]
Chibi Moon!
[grunting]
Mamoru! What's
wrong?
[grunting]
Chibi‐Usa!
Oh, no! Chibi Moon!
Chibi Moon!!
Behold, my queen, it
is done, just as you
commanded. I have
finally found the one
who possesses the
Golden Mirror.
Now Pegasus and the
Golden Crystal are
ours at last!
[laughing]
Let Chibi Moon go!
[chuckling]
At last, I will have
revenge for the years
of suffering
I've endured.
Feel the terror
of true darkness!
No matter how
powerful you are, we
will protect Chibi
Moon, Mamo, and
this planet!
Hm! What can you
do to stop me?
Next time on Sailor
Moon SuperS,
"Labyrinth of
Mirrors: Chibi Moon
Captured."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.