[thud]
Girls! It's time...
Where are you?
What's taking you?! Hurry
up and show yourselves!
(Cere‐Cere)
There's no need
to be so loud, Granny.
(Ves‐Ves)
It'll raise you're blood
pressure!
(Palla‐Palla)
You can't see us because we're
playing hide and seek!
(Zirconia)
Silence!
Owie...
Why do you have to
scream like that?
Gotcha, Palla‐Palla!
No fair! You cheated!
[laughter]
Good grief.
Where's Jun‐Jun?
She said she felt bored here,
so she went out to play.
Better than getting
scolded by an old hag.
[groan] You little...
So what do you want? Did you
find us a new target yet,
Granny?
Watch your attitude!
[grunt]
Hm? Blegh!
Oh, wow.
Seriously?
Sorry, he's not my type.
You think I care about that?
How much longer must I wait
before you bring me the Golden
Mirror?!
Until we get
the right target.
Palla‐Palla doesn't like this
boy at all. So Jun‐Jun can take
care of him.
That's a good idea.
Great! Now let's get
back to hide and seek.
Wait! I'm not done talking. You
little monsters, get back here,
this instant!
(Cere‐Cere)
Palla‐Palla, you're "it"!
(Palla‐Palla)
What? No fair...!
(Zirconia)
Oh, for heaven's sake& At this
rate, how are we ever going to
conquer the world?
♪
(Jun‐Jun)
What's going on down there?
Everybody's so busy
preparing for something.
Uh‐oh. Are they starting a
circus to compete with us?
...Oh, they better not!
(Kyusuke)
A bit more to the right.
Just a bit more&
More& There! That's the spot.
Huh?
Hey! Chibi‐Usa, don't go
home yet. Help us out.
What's with her?
(Usagi)
Overcome Your Fear: The
Jump to Freedom
[big sigh]
(Usagi)
Yoo‐hoo! Chibi‐Usa!
Hi!
Hey! You on your way home?
Hey guys...
Is tomorrow your
school's sports day?
Man, these things always
get me so pumped!
Mhm! And I'm already excited&
for the lunch you'll make us.
I have such great memories of
standing and cheering for my
favorite senior.
Especially when he ran in the
final relay! Y'know?
Oh, yeah!
I did that too!
(Thinking)
Sure, you guys get to joke
and relax 'cuz you're not
competing...
(Boy)
That's too dangerous!
[gasps]
(Kyusuke)
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
(Boy)
You sure?
Watch me! And Kyusuke
goes for the jump!
[gasps]
Woooo!
[sigh]
A perfect ten.
[cheering]
That boy is an amazing
athlete. Isn't he in
your class, Chibi‐Usa?
Kyusuke Sarashina&
Huh?
[thud]
You knucklehead! How many times
do I have to tell you to stop
pulling dangerous stunts like
that?!
Come see me in the teachers'
lounge later!
[cheering]
Yeesh...
Why did you do that?
'Cuz I called out to you,
but you didn't answer!
Why are you going home?
What's wrong?
You seem upset.
Don't you like sports day?
It isn't that...
...It's cuz part
of the obstacle course race
has a vaulting box on it.
Huh?
(Girl)
Drop it there!
And you... can't vault?
No...
What? Are you serious?
That's pretty lame!
It's just a vault.
[gasps]
Usagi, you of all people
shouldn't tease.
Why not?
Well, because
Usagi...can you vault?
What?! You've gotta be kidding
me! Of course, I can vault!
Wait&is vaulting
part of the race?
It sure is! You probably didn't
know because you were too busy
goofing off during practice.
Cool& Uh& Glad I didn't waste
time practicing since I've got
all the skills I need for the
obstacle course!
And don't try to ask
me for help.
I never said I wanted your help!
So that's just fine with me!
Yeah, I remember sports
day. That was fun.
[gasp] Mamo!
[groan]
Please! Can you teach me
how to do a vault...!
What are you doing!?
Nuh‐uh. I won't let you
ask Mamo to teach you.
Why not?!
Because we are on our way to do
some shopping together.
That means he doesn't have
any time for you. Heh heh...
Please, Mamo... I'm
begging you to teach me!
[hearty laugh]... no.
Are you saying you want me to
make a fool of myself in front
of everyone at school?!
This is a trial you must
overcome on your own.
Show us you can do it!
Wanna fight!?
Bring it on!
'kay, that's enough.
Why don't we help her, Usagi?
We don't have enough money to
spend, anyway.
Yeah, let's all do the vault.
Oh, thank you! Everyone!
No way!
Let's go to the
park so we can practice!
But I don't wanna!
(Minako)
well, we're doing it
so, get over it.
[nervous laugh]
(Jun‐Jun)
What is all this? They sure
went all out with the
decorations...
...this is going to be the
lamest circus ever,,,
Kyusuke is going for the jump!
[charging up yell]
No! It's too dangerous! Stop!
[screaming]
(Thinking)
Ever since that day, the vault's
been the only event I can't do.
Kyusuke, you can't
jump over the vault?!
[groan]
‐Seriously?
‐ You loser!
Shut up! No one's going to make
fun of me. I'm the best athlete
at school!
[charging up yell]
I can't do it!
I can't& I just
can't. Damn it!
What's with that guy?
Is someone watching me?
[gasp]
Whoa!
Awesome! I don't know who you
are, or where you're from,
but that was amazing!
[chuckle] Sup! So, having
problems with the vault?
[groan]
Want me to be your coach, kid?
Huh? Would you!
(Mamoru)
That's it? You just want
me to stand here?
[laugh] Yep, that's all!
Now remember Chibi‐Usa: You've
got to pick the right moment to
jump and place your hands.
I got it.
Ready!
Hold on... why do I
have to be the vault?
Quiet. Okay,
Chibi‐Usa! Let's go!
I don't like where
this is headed...
Now, go for it!
Humph!
Jump!
[happy gasp]
Yes! Like you're jumping into
the arms of your true love.
Wait! True what?!
Argh! Usagi, you idiot!
(Usagi)
I knew this would happen!
[shouting]
No! I just told you: find the
right moment to jump and place
your hands.
Right&
I don't get it. Why do you slow
down just before the point where
you're supposed to jump?
You'll never get over that
thing if you don't fix that.
[grunts]
Now, jump!
[flailing and screaming]
[sigh]
Why are you chickening out at
the same spot every time?!
I'm not chickening out.
[groan] It's getting late.
Let's call it a day.
What!? But I'm almost there!
A little more time? You gotta
help me.
If you're hungry, my family runs
a Soba noodle place. I'll treat
you to all you want!
dunno...
I have to be able to do the
vault by tomorrow. It
means everything to me.
Please! I'm begging you!
Look, it's getting dark so
we should stop for now.
Meet me here first thing
tomorrow morning.
Huh?
I've got a plan that'll have
you vaulting in no time.
[sigh] Thank you!
♪ Sailor Moon
(Chibi‐Usa)
Mamo& catch me in your
big, strong arms!
[whining]
I'll never get over that vault.
[gasp] Pegasus...!
Um&what were you doing?
Nothing! Just doing
some mental training.
Oh... The school sports day is
tomorrow, but I can't do the
vault...
You're lucky, Pegasus.
Flying is easy for you.
And you can do it anywhere
and anytime you want.
If only I could...
fly free...
What?
N‐nothing...
The truth is, when it comes to
flying, you possess much more
freedom than I do.
What? But I can't even
get over the vault!
You can do it.
I know you can.
(Usagi)
Chibi‐Usa!
We're starting early tomorrow
morning. Rei and the others are
gonna come to help out with your
training.
Ow! Now go to bed. Night!
Okay!
[birds chirping]
[shouting]
[screaming]
[groan] I've practiced for
hours but I can't get it.
Maybe I'm just hopeless.
[gasp] You came back!
Hmm...
Heh, what's up?
So it is you!
When I saw the photo last
night, I thought the face
looked really familiar.
Whew, what a relief!
Now that that's out of the
way, let's vault those
boxes and get it over with!
Kay,,,?
I noticed you're actually pretty
athletic. You're just a scared
baby about vaulting the box.
Am not...
Relax, it's cool.
I don't know what happened to
you in the past, but you'll
never jump the vault until you
overcome that fear of yours.
But how?
Don't worry& I came up with a
quick and easy way to rid you of
that ingrained fear of yours!
A “quick and easy way ”?
You heard me. Once you confront
something even more scary,
you'll forget your fear of
vaulting!
[snap]
Waaah!
W‐What's this?!
Huh? Hold on! Wait,
what's going on?!
This is what's going on!
[scream]
(Jun‐Jun)
[laugh] If you don't run,
it'll eat you alive!
Argh! This is crazy!
[panicking cries]
Argh!
I did it... I vaulted the
box! That was amazing!
But who cares about that!
The bear! Where did it go?
(Jun‐Jun)
[laugh] It was
just an illusion.
Guess it worked a
little too well.
An illusion? You mean
that bear and cage?
Scared you, didn't it?
Yeah, of course I was scared!
I thought I was going
to die! That's mean.
Kid, does it matter? I
mean, you were able to
jump over the vault.
And now& since your
dream has come true&
...it's time. Here goes!
Hm?
Orb shot!
[scream]
[shouting]
Huh? Are you kidding me?!
It's a blank mirror!
(Usagi / Chibi‐Usa)
Moon Crisis Make Up!
Mercury Crystal Power Make Up!
Mars Crystal Power Make Up!
Jupiter Crystal Power Make Up!
Venus Crystal Power Make Up!
♪
(Sailor Moon)
Hold it right there!
We came early to practice, only
to catch you in the act!
You're a nuisance to the
neighborhood, you know that?
We are the Pretty Guardians&
&who fight for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And I am Sailor Chibi Moon!
And in the name
of the Moon...
...we'll punish you!
You guys are like rats. You
keep popping up everywhere.
Oh well& Come forth, my
Lemures. Tobikiri Dude, the
dream‐eating acrobat!
Welcome! You guys want
to see me perform?
That must mean you all have
incredibly good taste in
flying feats of skill!
Okay, I will give it my best!
But before I do...
First things first!
Time to eat!
[gasp] Kyusuke!
Hey, now that you ate, get to
work and take out those girls!
Sure thing!
[grunts]
Here I come!
Mars Flame!
Sni...
[screams]
Like my fearless flying
routine? Let's go& again!
[screams]
Damn you! Jupiter...
No time for that!
He's moving too fast to let
us use our special attacks!
Well, at this rate, Tobikiri's
just gonna bore them to death.
Hey! Finish up and
clean this mess!
Okay, yes yes.
[screams]
At this rate we'll never
beat that monster.
Any ideas Mercury?
No, nothing yet&
[scream]
First we need to stop
him, even for a moment...
Yeah, but how&?
(Thinking)
If we don't beat him, Kyusuke
will lose his dream forever.
[wacky laugh]
Wait& I think I've got it!
Chibi Moon?!
I hope you're ready
for the big finale&!
[scream]
Here I come!
Stay away!
[scream]
What the hell!?
(All)
Chibi‐Moon!
(Pegasus)
You can do it.
I know you can.
(Thinking)
Right. Watch me, Pegasus!
Wait! What are you doing?!
[Attack yell]
Argh!
[grunt]
Chibi Moon...
She did it!
Let's end this, Sailor Moon!
[gasp] Right!
Please, Pegasus! Protect
everyone's dream!
Twinkle Yell!
[neigh]
Moon Gorgeous Meditation!
It's Stage Out for me! Buh bye!
Nice job, Chibi Moon!
Mhm!
...Get set!
[cheering]
Yah!
First place!
(All)
She did it!
[cheering]
(Announcer)
May I have your attention: The
next event is the boys' obstacle
race.
(Chibi‐Us)
Hey, Kyusuk!
...Go for the win!
Right!
[pow]
[crowd cheerin]
(Thinking)
I can do this vault!
I'm not scared anymore!
Woo‐hoo!
(Chibi‐Usa)
You did it, Kyusuke!
First place!
♪
(Usagi)
How's my portrait
coming along, Chibi‐Usa?
No pressure but you'd better
make me look beautiful!
(Chibi‐Usa)
Now look what you did! All your
talking made me mess up.
(Usagi)
Let me see!
(Usagi))
Wow, you suck! Your drawing is
all out of proportion. Even my
face is crooked.
(Chibi‐Usa)
Your face is crooked, Usagi!
(Usagi)
What?!
Next time on Sailor Moon SuperS,
"Don't Lose Sight of Your
Dreams: The Mirror of Truth."
(Usagi)
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.