[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[steps echoing]
[Sid] Lord Death has
made his decision.
This afternoon, you'll begin
class on a trial basis.
I'll come to get you later on,
so be sure you're ready...
You hear me?
Still nothing...
Look, I'm a zombie and
I still teach classes here.
So surely someone who's
still alive can make
a good student.
Hello in there!
[Sid sighs]
This kid totally hates me.
♪ opening song ♪
[Sid] I was talking to
him for a long time,
trying to persuade him to
come out, but he was too afraid.
In the end he told me
that because I was a zombie,
he didn't know
how to deal with me.
[Maka]
Okay... I see.
[Sid] He's incredibly
depressed...
...and I can't think
what else to do.
His room's down that way.
[Maka] So I finally
get to see Crona.
[Sid] You seem to have found
some way to connect to
and understand his
soul wavelength...
I'd like you to teach him
some things so he can
become more accustomed
to the academy.
It's no problem.
I'm happy to help out.
[Sid]
Thank you.
[Marie] I can't believe I'm
stranded in a place like this!
It's dark and drafty
down here...!
--[Marie] I'm cold! And hungry!
-[Sid] Oh, she
finally showed up.
Take her around the school
too while you're at it.
I'm just walking in circles.
Where'm I supposed to go?
[Marie squeals]
Sid, it's you!
Pardon me a second.
I was so lost I thought
I was gonna die here!
[Sid] You used to go to
this school too, Marie.
[Maka] The Exciting and
Embarrassing Trial Enrollment!
The DWMA New Lifestyle
Support Fair is Open?
[Stein thinks] Crona,
the Demon Swordsman.
A legacy of madness
left by the witch Medusa...
Who created a new form
of weapon and meister
when she melted down the
Demon Sword Ragnarok,
mixed him into black blood,
and used that blood
to replace Crona's own.
A witch's soul is needed
to turn a magic weapon
into a Death Scythe.
In the end,
perhaps it is the witch
who is responsible for the
evolution of the weapon,
and not the weapon's meister.
You can't stand it,
can you Stein?
Why hold it in?
That's not healthy.
You want to
dismember everything...
You can't hide it from me.
You're curious about him...
You want to study
the child I created.
[Stein breathes heavy]
[Medusa] You've been infected
by the Kishin's madness.
I can't wait to
see what happens.
[Knock on metal door]
[Maka]
Coming in...!
Hey, uh--
There's no one here.
[Crona]
Maka.
[Maka] What're you
doing over there?
I feel safer when I'm
tucked in the corner like this.
Come on, you look like
somebody's given
you a time out...
Here, stand up.
Yeah, okay.
I'm going to show you
around the academy today.
Oh, you are...?
Um, I dunno...
You know I'm really happy
to have you here, Crona.
[Crona]
Yeah.
[Marie]
Hey, hey!
And this lady is Ms. Marie.
I'm new here too...
Well, I'm new as
a teacher anyway.
Tomorrow is my first day...
I know how you feel, Crona.
We're in the same boat...
But don't worry.
I'm sure we'll
both do just fine.
Oh... okay.
Oh, I see now...
show him he's not alone...
A nice technique, Marie.
Crona?
[Sid] The blue man
is back again...!
He scares me!
Sid, we need you
to stay out here.
You can relax.
I know Sid there looks
like big, scary blue gorilla...
But I promise,
he's actually a pretty nice guy.
'Kay...
[Marie]
All right then.
We don't want to keep
your education waiting
any more, now do we...?
Let's get going.
[Ragnarok] I wouldn't be gettin'
too cocky now if I were you,
stupid humans!
[Ragnarok]
Yah!
[Crona]
Hi there, Mini-Ragnarok.
[Marie] Aw, what is that?
It's so cute!
What'd you do to me,
you ugly cow?
I don't know what you mean.
What're you doing here?
I never agreed to
be your friend!
Ahhh...
I'm feeling so much closer
to you now that
you can't hurt me.
[Ragnarok cries out]
[Maka gasps]
[Ragnarok]
You don't have much to
look at under there,
do you...? Cow!
[Crona]
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to.
--I'll never do it again,
I promise.
--No, Crona, it's okay.
--Just please don't hit me.
--Please don't hit me! It hurts!
--I'm the one
who should apologize!
[Maka] Come on Crona.
Quit hiding...
There's nothing
to be afraid of here.
It's... so bright.
[Crona] What?
Why're you laughing?
Did I say something funny?
[Soul] Well... How do you like
our humble academy so far?
Do you think you can
get used to being here?
No, this place is
definitely not for me.
You're just a little nervous...
You'll be fine. Don't worry.
[Crona] Uh-uh...
I can't deal with this...
I wanna go back to my corner!
Maybe a nice,
hard kick would help!
[Maka]
Down boy! Quit it.
Oh hey! I know!
Why not write some poetry?
How does that sound?
Poetry?
You gotta be kidding me!
[Soul laughs]
[Maka] I write poems a lot when
something's bothering me.
It really helps.
Oh, come on!
How much more emo
can you possibly get...?
You can talk to me if
something's wrong, you know!
Why don't we try
writing a poem together?
If you say so,
I guess I can give it a try.
[Crona]
D-d-d-d-d-d
Are you all done?
Yeah.
I wanna see.
This is so stupid.
So uh... how is it?
[Maka] This makes me wish
I'd never been born.
[Marie]
It's so... sad.
Hi-ya guys!
What're you lame-o's
doing in here?
The weather's amazing!
We shouldn't be
locked up in school!
Let's get going!
Well. I guess it
does get gloomy
without Black Star around...
But fear not,
now that I'm here...
The sun has come out
from behind the clouds!
[Soul]
Read this.
[Black Star] I wish
I'd never been born.
What's so horrible
about a stupid poem?
[Soul] I wish that I'd
never been born.
[Crona] I wish that I'd
I wish that I'd never
come back to life.
What the hell?
Sid, when did you get in here?
[Sid]
Uhh... about Crona...
...there are still some
issues to work out...
But I do think
he'll get accustomed
to the academy eventually.
[Death] Ooh good!
I'm glad to hear it...!
But you're looking
a little pale, Sid...
Do you think you're coming
down with something?
Oh, no...! No, it's nothing.
Anyway, Crona is headed for
the Czech Republic right now.
I sent him along as part of
Maka's supplementary lesson.
Why, what's wrong over there?
[Sid] There's a village where
the citizens spend their time
creating figures
known as golems...
Apparently, the oldest golem
made there has suddenly gone
berserk and begun
destroying things...
Luckily the damage so
far seems to be light.
Hold on a sec,
are you for real, Sid?
For real about what?
[Death]
When golems are created,
they're programmed
to be protectors...
Whether the damage is
light so far or not,
the implications
here are serious.
For a golem to lose control
and begin destroying
things is unthinkable.
It may have something to do
with the madness wavelengths.
Sid, contact Stein...
This could be very important...
I'd like to hear his
opinion on the matter.
[Maka] So this is
Loof Village, huh...?
They sure do have
a lot of chimneys.
[Soul] That's because they
make so many golems here.
There's probably a
kiln in every house.
[Ragnarok] Now let's
eat us some souls!
Things have changed.
That isn't how
we operate anymore...
We're gonna do things
differently now that
we're students at the academy.
[shaking impact]
I wonder where this
supposedly berserk golem
that we need to find is hiding.
I'll ask the
villagers for details.
[Soul thinks] These golem
creators are enchanters...
They use those giant gloves
of theirs to mix
magic into the soil...
That's how they create the
figures and bring them to life.
I can't say they look
all that happy to see
us in their village.
[Maka]
Soul...!
No one I talked to knows
anything about the golem.
They're hiding somethin',
that's for sure.
[Giriko]
Hey. You guys.
I'm guessin' you're here because
you heard about our incident...
You're looking for the golem,
the one that's gone berserk?
My name's Giriko...
I'm an enchanter...
I'll show you the way.
Just follow me.
[typing on keyboard]
What're you doing sitting
here in the dark?
[Marie]
Hey, Stein.
Hey, do you hear me?
Marie.
[Marie]
You okay?
[Stein]
Yeah, I'm fine...
What do you need?
[Marie] I have a message
from Lord Death...
Apparently the oldest golem in
Loof Village has gone crazy.
Do you have any cups?
I'll make us some tea.
Use those over there.
You put tea in a beaker?
Anyway, Lord Death wants to
hear your opinion
on the subject.
Is this incident going to
be a problem for us?
Golems are usually constructed
to protect against evil...
It isn't in their programming to
become destructive like this.
I suppose modern technology
could be used to create golems
with different programming.
But then again you said this
happened to the oldest golem
they have in the village.
[Marie] You think the
madness wavelengths
have something to do with it?
Even if they do, the order
of events seems strange.
How do you mean?
Thankfully as far as we know...
there still haven't been
any incidents related to the
Kishin's revival and madness.
It's hard to believe that
the first such incident would
involve a soulless creature
like the golem going crazy.
I agree. If anything it seems
like people should be the
first to be affected by it...
So the first event we hear
about shouldn't involve
an object like the golem.
[Stein] That's right...
The golems shouldn't go
berserk until the world is fully
enveloped in the
madness of the Kishin.
Of course, we still shouldn't
take the situation too lightly.
Hold on a sec.
I'm going to the library...
Please ask Lord Death
to give me some time
to consider what's happened.
And after all that
work to make us tea!
[Soul]
Hey... how much further
do we have to go until
we reach the golem?
[Giriko]
We're almost there.
Yeah right. That's what
you keep telling us.
You and your village are
really starting to
creep me out, dude.
[Maka]
Be quiet, Soul...
There's no need to be rude.
[Giriko] The villagers here make
their living by creating golems
and exporting them
to other countries...
The golems ward off evil
if you put them
by your front door...
You see, everyone is
afraid of the unknown.
So what you're trying
to say now is that we're evil?
Why are you getting
so angry with him...?
He never said
anything like that.
[Soul] Not in so
many words maybe,
but that's
what they're thinking.
[Goriko] The truth is, we want
to live in peace and quiet...
We don't like it much
when strangers
come to our village.
Which is why we try to
adopt the calm of the
golem and avoid conflict.
In the end,
everyone is the same...
We all have evil inside us...
Even someone who
wears a mask of goodness...
can still have pitch
darkness in his heart, you see.
[shaking impact]
What was that--?
Oh come on...
...if I tell you,
that'll spoil all the fun.
Oh well. I suppose there's
no hiding the truth anymore.
Heads up, Soul...
Yeah, I'm already on it.
[Maka] Impossible...!
That's crazy!
[Soul]
What's up, Maka?
[Maka]
What's going on...?
Golems aren't supposed to
be living things, are they...?
But I can sense
a soul wavelength
coming from that thing!
You're a young meister,
I take it...
Looks like you
figured it out.
[Giriko] I've been waiting
for this moment...
...for eight hundred years.
I used techniques I learned
as an enchanter to swap
my memories with
my own children's,
passing my brain
through the generations.
I've lived out
thirty boring lives.
Eight hundred years...?
What are you talking about?
[Giriko]
The idea was to store up
enough strength to
take on Death...
...and his precious
organization...
...your DWMA.
But that's all over now...
I think you children might want
to start saying your goodbyes.
What the hell is he?
You see, I don't need a meister.
The golem I created for
myself will do just fine.
[Soul]
This guy's a weapon?
[Maka]
And his golem has a soul.
What else is wrong
with this village?
Give up your attack
and turn away right now.
If you do continue
to fight me...
...then I'll take your soul...
You got it?
[Giriko] My engine isn't
even running yet.
[chainsaw revving up]
[Crona]
Maka!
His wavelength is distorted.
It's full of bloodlust.
[Giriko]
Now that I'm good and
fired up, there'll
be no stopping us!
[roars]
[Giriko]
My soul's wavelength holds
eight hundred years
of anger and hatred...!
I've been wearing this same
forced smile on
my face for generations.
I had to be nice to stay
under the academy's radar.
My life so far has been
nothing but meaningless crap...!
Boring... empty... crap!
My life is a pointless cesspool!
[Maka cries out]
Maka!
Damn it.
[Giriko laughs]
Smiling so long...
I don't remember what
my real self is like...
Tell me who I am again?
Think think think.
It's gotta be in
there somewhere...
Oh yeah. I think
I may have it now!
Everything I am,
everything I've made
myself into, has to go!
It's got to be destroyed!
I'll obliterate it all!
That golem is too big
for me to fight effectively...
I know I need to
attack it from a distance...
...except I don't know how
to do that using a scythe.
[Ragnarok] There is Crona's
Screech Arrow, you know.
Just thought I'd mention that...
Don't know why though...
We're onlookers...
No way we're gonna help you...
Not even for three
pieces of candy.
[Crona]
Ragnarok?
Then how 'bout four?
[Ragnarok] It was just a
figure of speech...!
I don't actually
want any candy at all...
I'm not a baby, you idiot!
Six pieces, okay?!
[Ragnarok] It's not
a matter of number!
Fifteen then...!
I'll give you as many
candies as you want!
[Ragnarok]
Really?!
Maka Albarn...!
You know how to
strike a good bargain...!
It pays to negotiate,
don't you think?
The first speed setting
doesn't tear him to pieces?
Well that's disappointing.
[Ragnarok] Don't
underestimate my black blood!
[Ragnarok cries out]
Goo-bee!
[Maka thinks] How did I ever
manage to fight that thing?
I'm real glad he's
on our side now.
Now Ragnarok.
You seem a little shorter
than you used to be.
Sure you can handle this?
Quit your worrying... dumbass!
[Crona] Don't hurt
Maka anymore...
If something's bothering you,
why not write a poem?
We can write one together, okay?
[Crona]
Here we go Maka.
[Maka]
Right.
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] I wish I'd
never been born.
[Sid]
I wish I'd never come back.
[Maka] I wish I could learn
how to enjoy sushi.
[Sid] I wish I didn't have
a hole in my head.
[Maka]
I wish I wasn't hot-tempered.
[Sid]
I wish I didn't have blue skin.
[Maka]
I wish I didn't have fat ankles.
[Sid]
I wish I didn't have bad breath.
[Maka]
Yeah... we all wish that.
[Sid] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
"800 Years of Bloodlust...
Advent of the Heretic Witch?"
[Maka]
Watch it or...
...you'll wish you had.