[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Grandwitch]
Joma joma dabarasa.
As Grandwitch, I now declare
this witches' mass open...
Let us begin.
[crowd]
Joma joma dabarasa.
Crona... Ragnarok...
come along.
[Crona]
Yes ma'am, Lady Medusa.
♪ opening song ♪
Hold on a moment.
Oh dear.
Ah! What's happening?
She won't let us go...
I don't think I know how
to deal with this situation.
You can deal with it by
shutting up and giving
me all your money.
[Medusa]
Good evening, Eruka Frog...
Did you need something?
Ribbit.
[Mizune]
(Chee-chee-chee)
I think you know
why I'm stopping you.
Oh, yes... But come on,
it's not as if I'm the
only one who brought
non-witches to the
gathering tonight...
Over there...
That little witch is
accompanied by a human.
So you see, it's not just me.
[Angela] Mifune, I'm starting
to get hungry.
The purity of the
witches' mass certainly
has gone downhill.
But that isn't what
I wanted to talk to
you about tonight, Medusa...
I have some
questions for you.
First, what were you doing
stealing something from
the Grandwitch's room?
And second... You snuck yourself
onto the staff at the DWMA...
Why in the world
would you do that?
Crona, give me my coat.
Yes, right away,
Lady Medusa.
[Medusa] My research
at the academy
has been fully approved
as you well know...
The Grandwitch herself
is on my side Eruka.
[Eruka]
Just a minute!
The Grandwitch's
eyesight is failing.
She doesn't see what a
nuisance you've made
of yourself lately.
That academy is there
to hunt down witches.
You know that as well as I do.
If you slip up just once...
...you won't be the
only one in trouble,
you'll take us down with you.
And then there's him...
Why would you try to
create a Kishin that could
potentially be an
enemy to our kind?
You've taken it too far...
It's time for you to stop.
Medusa] You meddlesome little
frog and mouse.
I think I'm going to
have to punish you.
R-Ribbit
[Medusa] Perhaps not
right now, though...
I'm in a hurry.
With so many
students to look after,
the school nurse
mustn't be late.
Joma joma dabarasa.
I can't stand that witch...
Stupid snake woman.
[Maka] Courage
That Beats Out Fear
~Maka Albarn's
Great Resolution?~
[Medusa]
Turn around for me.
And tell me how
you've been feeling.
More or less normal, I guess...
Except for, lately,
I've been having this really
weird dream over and over again.
A strange dream you say?
Yeah...And it's been
bothering me because
I can remember it so clearly...
I always start out in this
room that's pitch-black.
[jazz music playing]
[Soul] There's a record player,
and it's always skipping
like the record's
scratched or something...
The music that's playing is
some kinda jazz song that
I think I've heard before
but can't really place...
After I've been
sitting there for a bit...
...this guy always appears
from the other
side of the room...
He's a little demon wearing
a fancy suit and dancing
this weird dance out of
time with the music.
[Demon]
Swing swing swing.
Dude, this is jazz.
It isn't swing music.
[Demon] But jazz is so much more
appropriate for nighttime.
Far as I know,
music's not picky about
when it gets played...
You can decide,
so why not listen to swing?
That's right the
decision's mine...Yes sir.
You can decide too.
You're eligible.
[Demon] When you were cut open
like a fish being gutted,
you must have
been afraid. Am I right?
And wouldn't it be nice
to have a strong mind,
one that can get rid
of the fear you feel?
[Soul] If you forget your fear,
you'll become reckless.
That's something they
teach at the academy.
[Demon] (heh)... What kind of
fool are you...?
Do you think you're in
heaven where you
can't get hurt again...?
Hate to break it to you,
but you're still on Earth...
And if you want to
stay alive down here,
you're going to need more
power than you've got now...
Power so overwhelmingly strong
you can say goodbye
to all your fears.
You're nothing
without that power.
Now come on and
get out there already.
No, wait. Hold on a second.
Please I don't want
to leave this room.
Let me stay here until the
dream is over and I wake up.
I'll even put up
with the lame music!
[Demon] Seek out
the power you need.
Find a rule to break.
It will make you stronger.
Stronger, perhaps,
than you thought possible.
What makes you so afraid
of leaving the room, Soul?
[door creaks and shuts]
[Soul] When I leave the room,
the darkness continues...
Then all of a sudden
I see this light...
and I move toward it...
but when I go through...
[Soul cries out]
When I go through, I'm
coming out of Maka's stomach.
Interesting... The black blood
that's entered his body seems
to be having an effect on him.
So... Aside from all that,
how am I doing?
Well... you still have a
slight arrhythmia,
but you seem to be
making a nice recovery so far.
Let's just take
your blood pressure.
As for this strange
dream of yours...
It's not unusual to have
recurring nightmares after
going through the
trauma that you have.
I don't think you
need to be worried...
Is that all, or was there
something else you've
been concerned about?
Well, I dunno if 'concerned'
is the right word
for it, exactly.
But ever since we
got back from Italy...
Maka's been acting all strange.
I think something's
been bothering her.
[Medusa] Really...?
I'm sorry to hear that.
[Black Star]
A jar?
That's right. A jar.
Is it a special jar?
Nope. Nothing special.
It's just an ordinary jar...
Now, the water that's
inside the jar is
another story altogether.
It's called soul-sapping
water because it sucks
out your soul wavelength.
Compared to that,
the jar's very
ordinary indeed...
Go on, try sticking your
hand in the water.
[Black Star] All right, but I'm
still a little iffy
about this jar.
[Soul]
What was that?!
I knew that jar was dangerous.
[Stein]
No, it's just the water.
You might want to start off
by sticking in only
one finger at a time.
All I have to do is get
to where I can withstand
putting my whole
hand in there...
and then I can use Tsubaki's
Enchanted Sword mode, Professor?
That's the basic idea.
That'll be a nice break...
All I've been doing lately
is muscle conditioning,
and it's gettin old.
What's with you?
It isn't fair.
How can you get stronger
just by playing with
a jar filled with water?
Hah! Isn't it obvious?
I'm Black Star...
I'm on a whole different
level than you.
I'm a big man.
I've beaten Death!
Who else can say that?
No fair...! Professor Stein,
can I have one of
those special jars too,?
[Stein]
I can't do that.
The water in the jar is
only intended to help
Black Star be able to use
Tsubaki's Enchanted Sword mode.
[Black Star] I'm not gonna let
myself get beaten by a jar.
I don't care how special it is!
[Stein] I'd be surprised if
Black Star even realized
what he was doing by
saying things like that...
By talking constantly about
what a star he is
and how 'big' he is,
Black Star is actually driving
himself without even meaning to.
[Maka]
Driving himself?
[Stein]
Yes.
"There's no stage
too big for me.
Of course I can do it!"...
That's his answer to
any challenge he faces.
And once he's said that,
he will put every effort
into making it happen,
because he's already
decided he will succeed.
Black Star is trying
to surpass death.
He is bound to become stronger.
Right.
But that's his way
of making himself stronger.
It's not a method that
will work for everybody...
You have to find your
own way to do it,
something that works for you.
My own way of
becoming stronger.
Right now you're definitely
lacking something, Maka.
A certain level of stress and
anxiety is understandable.
But you don't want
to take it too far.
Wait, what do you
mean 'lacking something'?
Once you figure
out what it is,
come see me and we'll
decide what to do about it.
Didn't I tell you to start out
with only one finger.
You can take
the jar with you...
The lesson's over for now.
[Blair]
Hey, Maka...
What about the party?
[Maka]
Oh yeah! I almost forgot.
I was gonna throw a
party to congratulate Tsubaki
and Black Star
since they finally
managed to collect a soul...
and to celebrate the
fact that Soul's coming home.
Be sure to have some
good fish dishes, okay?
He's strong, huh?
Medusa] Okay, Soul...
I expect to see you
back here in one week.
[knocking at door]
Excuse me.
Hey.
I'm going home to get
ready for the party.
See you there.
Something does seem to be
bothering her. Is it the scar?
Yeah, that happens
every time she sees it.
She gets this pained look.
Well it may not've been tasty,
but it sure was filling.
Hey, I've got an idea...
Next time you do the cooking.
Don't listen to him, Maka.
It was delicious.
Yum...! Yum!
Yeah, thank you
for the snacks.
You guys have
a nice place here.
It's so tidy...
You must make a
point of keeping it clean.
It helps that Maka yells
at me whenever
I make a mess.
Is it just the two of
you living here, then?
[Blair] Yoo-hoo! Is everyone
having a good time?
Which one of you little boys
wants to come and
take a bath with me?
The water's nice and warm.
Is it always like
this over here?
Oh yeah... Anybody want
to take the sexy kitty home?
She's free.
[Medusa thinking] Infiltrating
the academy was worth the risk.
I'll need to run some tests
on Soul now that he has
Ragnarok's black
blood inside him.
With this key,
it should be easy.
[Medusa]
Well...
What a coincidence
running into you here.
[Eruka] Have you already guessed
what we're doing here, Medusa?
Or should I tell you?
Oh, please... tell me.
Ribbit-ribbit...
All right then, I will...
We've come here to kill you.
Oh no! But that's terrible...!
I thought we were friends.
Don't take it personally.
We simply have no interest
in attracting the attention
of the Grim Reaper...
...and we don't
care for whatever
little experiments you're
doing at the academy either...
You're now a liability Medusa.
[Medusa] And
liabilities must be killed.
Before you do that, though...
may I offer you a
little piece of advice?
That outfit is
a liability, too...
It simply screams 'witch.'
Whether you're casting
Soul Protect or not,
there are a good number of
young meisters wandering
these streets, who know
a witch when they see one.
[Eruka] Sweet of you to warn us,
but don't you worry...
If it comes to it,
we can use our
transformation
magic to escape...
...which is a luxury
you don't have.
I see now...
So that's how you're
planning to beat me, is it?
We know we couldn't beat
you in a fight under
ordinary circumstances...
But here in Death City you need
to maintain your
cover as a school nurse.
You can't drop your Soul Protect
and use magic
to defend yourself.
That would be a dead giveaway.
You're cornered.
All we have to do is attack you
while you're
using Soul Protect...
If you don't fight back,
we'll defeat you easily.
And if you do release your
Soul Protect to attack us,
we'll transform and
make a clean escape.
Meanwhile, you'll be revealed
to the meisters as a witch
and they'll hunt you down.
Whatever you decide
to do, we still win.
Not a bad plan,
wouldn't you say...?
And that's how the
frog and mouse will
beat the snake...
Tonight you'll be the
one croaking, not me...
Funny how the world works.
If you're going to kill me,
please don't make me
listen to your bad jokes first.
That's just plain cruel.
Soul Protect... release.
You're finished...
Say goodbye, now.
That soul wavelength...
Witch.
What's up Maka?
You startled us.
It's two witches...
What are they
doing in Death City?
Sorry guys. I'll be right back.
Hey Maka, what gives?
I would love nothing more
than to hear your screams
as you're writhing in agony.
But I'm afraid we don't
have time for that...
How unfortunate.
[Medusa] You do have the
brains of a frog and a mouse.
Only stupid creatures would
try to defeat me this way.
You will be punished.
Too bad you aren't even fit
to serve as research subjects.
If you're going to fight
all we have to do is run.
What is she waiting for...?
Why isn't she releasing
her Soul Protect?
Wait a second...!
Where are the tattoos that
were on your shoulder?
Oh my... They seem to have
disappeared, haven't they?
[Mizune makes
"chee chee" noises]
Mizune what's wrong?
The snakes...!
You put them
inside of Mizune's body?!
There's no way...
When could you have--
You did it last night.
I have thousands of snakes
stored in my body waiting
to do whatever I say.
Those are only a few of them.
Mizune!
My snakes will consume her
until there's nothing left.
But how could you?
The snakes are magic too,
aren't they...?
And you haven't
released your Soul Protect...!
So how are you...?
[Medusa] These little ones
have magic of their own...
I don't have to release my
Soul Protect to use them.
This one's my pride and joy...
She's such an obedient
and effective little darling.
An impressive trick...
Wouldn't you say?
[Medusa] You must
realize by now...
Mizune isn't the only one my
darlings have slithered inside.
R-R Ribbit.
[footfalls]
[Eruka Frog runs off crying]
[Medusa]
That didn't take long...
Stein.
And Maka.
Are you all right Dr. Medusa?
We detected two witches
in this area and came
as quickly as we could.
Yes... I sensed them too and
came here to investigate
them myself.
I wonder if one of them
could have been the witch
who was there when
Soul was injured.
That is a possibility.
[Stein] No, I don't think
it's the same one.
For one thing, that witch had
the Demon Sword and its
meister along with her.
And even if she had been here,
I doubt we would
have sensed her at all...
I have a feeling that this one
is too cunning to release her
Protect in the middle of
Death City without reason.
One thing we do know
is that this witch has an
interest in weapons
and meisters...
...so I wouldn't be surprised
if she was in the area,
observing the students here.
But I have no doubt she
would want to do it quietly.
Yes...
I suppose it's even possible
that she has managed to
infiltrate the academy itself...
But that would be tricky,
even for a powerful witch.
Whatever the case,
it's a relief that you weren't
hurt by these witches,
Dr. Medusa...
We would be in some serious
trouble if anything happened
to our only school nurse.
[Medusa]
Thanks, but I'm fine.
But still... If I...
...ever see that sword
and its meister again...
[Maka thinks] I don't know how
much longer I can handle this...
I know I promised myself
I'd become stronger, but...
[footfalls]
[Soul]
Maka!
Are you all right, Maka...?
You shouldn't take
off on your own.
It's too dangerous!
I'm fine, Soul.
Hmm?
[Maka thinks]
I couldn't do it...
I couldn't bring myself
to look at Soul's scar.
I have to find a way
to face this scar...
I can't let Soul get
hurt like that again.
I refuse to let my
fear control me anymore.
You have to tell me
what's going on.
All right, Professor Stein.
Yes?
I know...
what I'm lacking now.
You told me to
figure it out, and I have.
Very good.
[Stein thinks]
At last...
Maka's finally found the
courage to fight her fear.
[Stein] In that case,
I'd like you and Soul
to come to my office
tomorrow for a special lesson.
[boing boing boing]
I've come far enough.
I should be able
to rest a bit now.
Next time I really am
going to kill you,
Medusa. Ribbit!
Ah, yes...
That feels nice and
cool on my foot.
I could get used to this.
[Eruka Frog]
That's her isn't it?
I thought I was safe.
There's just one tiny favor
I need to ask of you, Eruka.
[Eruka]
A key?
I don't understand.
How did you know where I was?
The snakes inside you told me...
It doesn't matter
how far you run.
From now on,
I'll know wherever you go.
[Medusa]
Now about that favor...
There's a man I'd like you
to release using that key.
His witch prison
number is thirteen.
Unless you're
a very stupid frog,
I'm sure you know
who I'm talking about.
[Eruka] You don't mean the
man with the Magic Eye?!
But, he's the one who
took the
Grandwitch's left eye...!
If I free him I'll be banished
from the witch world forever!
No...!
They'll probably just kill me!
[Medusa] I can kill you right
here if you'd prefer.
[Eruka]
Ribbit! Fine! I'll do it.
There's a little experiment
I'm going to do using the
man with the magic eye...
Some questions I have
concerning Soul Eater.
You're going to use
him for an experiment...?!
What are you thinking...?
You're out of your mind...!
Ribbit.
You don't feel as
good on my foot now...
Change yourself
back into a frog.
[Eruka]
O...kay.
[Prisoner A] Plus two plus one
plus two plus one plus two...
He's at it again...
That's getting so annoying.
What is the answer?
How many times did I multiply?
One plus two plus
one plus two plus one...
Tell me the answer.
How many times did I multiply?
You're just in there
adding ones and twos...
You haven't
multiplied anything yet.
[Free bellows]
[Guard]
Whoa!
[Free]
I can't see...
I can't see anything.
It's been ages since
I've seen a good comedy...
♪ closing song ♪
[Medusa] While the kids
weren't paying attention,
I took over the preview...!
Next time we'll begin a
much better show starring me...!
It will be called
"Pretty Dr. Medusa"...
Warning: Content may not be
appropriate for
children of all ages.
On the next episode of "Pretty--
[Maka]
Witch hunter!
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Man With the Magic Eye...
Soul and Maka's
Diverging Soul Wavelength?
[Medusa] Nake Snake
Cobra Cobra...
Get out of this preview...
It's mine!
[Maka]
No...! Impossible!