[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Death] The Magic Tool Brew is
located on an island north
of Alaska known as Lost Island.
This island was previously
home to a Magic Tool facility
created and
operated by witches...
However, an accident occurred,
causing a great explosion,
and the facility was destroyed.
[explosion]
[Death] That same accident
created a strong magnetic field
in the center of the island...
The magnetism is so powerful
that the entire area
remains inaccessible...
This is where the tool
known as Brew,
or The Tempest, is located.
There are serious consequences
for anyone who stays
inside the field for too long...
Fortunately, this difficulty
applies to our enemies too.
The longest anybody may
safely remain within the
magnetic field is
twenty minutes...
Which means not only
will we be fighting
Arachnophobia
for possession of Brew...
We will be battling
against time, as well.
♪ opening song ♪
[Marie] As you know,
our mission here
is to acquire
the Magic Tool Brew.
You were briefed on the
battle plan a few days ago...
Does everyone remember?
We do.
[Marie] While Sid's squad moves
to head off Arachnophobia,
we'll make for the center
of the island's magnetic field,
where Brew is lying dormant.
However, only Marie and I
will actually be
entering the field itself...
The rest of you are not to
set foot inside the field.
You will stay outside,
awaiting our return.
This may be the
biggest battle you've seen...
Remember, you were chosen
because you're the elite
among all one star meisters...
Fight well.
Don't prove our choice wrong.
Let's go and burn
these guys up.
[Maka]
The Battle For Brew...!
Clash, The DWMA vs.
Arachnophobia?o~
[Arachnid 1] Mosquito!
We've sighted the enemy
at the east end of the island!
They're just in time.
Today we capture
Brew for the Lady Arachne!
[cheers]
[Soldier 1] Captain...
take a look at that.
[Sid] It's all
that's left of the
witches' Magic Tool facility...
Looks like the explosion
completely leveled the place.
Keep your wits about you.
The magnetic field interferes
with soul resonance along
with electronic communication.
[Soldier 1]
Got it.
[Sid]
What the...?
They're here already?
Everyone, back in formation!
[Azusa] Sid...! Check out the
group in the ruins below you!
What about them?
That samurai from before!
He's taken down almost
all of our troops.
Well done as always...
I love those
sharp eyes of yours.
Naigus!
I'm going hunting...
You stay here and see that
the troops have their orders,
then head for
the designated point.
[Naigus]
I'm on it.
Let's go, Azusa.
[Azusa]
Roger.
So it's finally started.
So cold...
I came here ready
for a good fight...
...but I wasn't counting
on this weather.
A man could freeze
to death out here.
Someone worth fighting
had better show up quickly.
[Giriko yawns]
I'll turn into an icicle pretty
soon if I don't get moving.
Hey, I think I heard
something back there.
Yeah, like a low,
rumbling sound...
Giriko look over there!
[Man B cries out]
What the hell?!
[Man B]
An avalanche!
I apologize...! I turned my
music up, and the
vibrations seemed to
have caused an avalanche.
Not this guy?!
It looks like I've stumbled
across some enemy troops.
[Troops cry out]
Triple Speed!
Saw Leg!
[Man]
We're gonna die!
Oh, God...
Have mercy on my
precious snowmobile...
It was swallowed by
the avalanche.
Get outta that tree,
you stupid bastard...
I'm going to saw
you into pieces.
Oh, my...
...we meet again, do we?
The magnetic field...
It's a big one, all right.
Marie and I are the only ones
continuing on from here...
Remember the instructions
I gave you earlier.
Stay put until we get back.
Listen, Kim...
We should be back
here in twenty minutes...
If not, use Jacqueline to
send a signal to the rest
of the academy troops...
Then follow the tracks
left by Sid's group,
meet up with the other troops,
and get off this island.
[Maka]
But Professor, what will
happen to you and
Marie if you're left behind?
Arachnophobia will
be in there too...
Shouldn't we go in with you...?
You guys might need our help.
More people only
means a bigger battle.
And the bigger the battle,
the longer it's going to last...
Too long... and both sides
will be lost inside
of the field...
I would've thought the
situation was fairly obvious...
Certainly to a student at
the top of her class, anyway.
No need to be worried...
With Marie and me
working together,
it won't matter how many
enemies we encounter,
we'll be out in
five minutes or less.
With that said, we're off.
Wish us luck, everybody!
We can't win.
He's too strong.
He deflected it...!
Those're some amazing reflexes!
[Sid] He's even faster
than I thought!
Careful Sid...!
He's catching up!
Right. On it.
Here, have another!
Catch us if you can, samurai.
[Mifune]
Let's go.
[Maka]
Jacqueline's so warm!
[Kim] I should start
charging for this.
Is that a chocolate bar...?
Kilik, be a pal and
share some of it.
Sorry. There's only
enough for me.
Liar!
You have more! I saw it!
Keep your hands off my candy!
Hand it over!
How long has it been now...?
They said they wouldn't be
gone longer than five minutes.
They still have
fifteen minutes to go.
Hey, what's bothering you?
[Maka]
Professor Stein's and
Miss Marie's
wavelengths just vanished.
You've been able to sense
their soul wavelengths,
even in a magnetic
field that strong?
The static is loud.
I only get a spark
here and there.
But I can tell
something isn't right.
Hey, what's bothering you?
[Maka]
Professor Stein's and
Miss Marie's
wavelengths just vanished.
You've been able to sense
their soul wavelengths,
even in a magnetic
field that strong?
The static is loud.
I only get a spark
here and there.
But I can tell
something isn't right.
Alright... then I'll go
in and check it out.
Since I'm a Grim Reaper,
my body shouldn't be
affected too much by the field.
No, Kid...
It isn't safe to go alone.
Come on.
In that case, we'll go too.
Yeah.
[Ox] What about the
professor's orders?
He was very explicit.
[Kim] I can't come,
or there won't
be anyone here
to send a signal.
[Ox] At any rate, it doesn't
look like we're alone anymore.
Perfect.
No worries.
We can take care of them.
You guys get
inside the field.
Leave them to us.
[Troops cry out]
[Ox] You want to challenge
the Royal Thunder?
Bad idea.
As you will no doubt realize...
You can't win.
I'll protect my
dear Kim at all costs...
Does my manly display
impress you, sweetheart?
I'd be more impressed if
you were rich and handsome.
Does nobody appreciate
my massive intellect?
You aren't getting past me
without paying the toll, boys.
I can't go in there and
leave my team behind
to fight these guys...
Tell ya what, Black Star...
Take this... for energy.
Candy bar...! A warm and
comforting treat in a bleak,
freezing cold wasteland!
[Kilik]
Just take it.
We'll be back.
[Kilik]
Now then...
Let's warm up this party.
Thunder!
Ready for Soul Resonance!
Aphex... Twin!
[explosion]
Let's go.
[Maka]
Man, you guys move fa--
What...? When we were
looking in from outside,
the building seemed to
be completely destroyed.
Now it's whole.
I still can't sense
the professor's soul...
...or Miss Marie's...
Maybe they went
inside the pyramid.
Hey...! Look up
there in the sky!
It looks like--!
That's impossible!
But he's always said
he can't leave the city!
[Maka]
It's Lord Death!
But... he doesn't
look right somehow.
That's how my dad
used to look back
before he started the academy.
Things were a
lot different then.
I still don't get
what's going on...
Why's he here?
Come on. We need to hurry
and see what's
happening over there.
Good luck little Mizune!
The DWMA
versus Arachnophobia...
Whoever wins,
we still come out on top.
I never knew being chased by
a samurai could
be this exciting?
[Mifune]
Damn zombie.
Did I miss him?
[Azusa]
What happened, Sid?
Are you okay?
Just a scratch, that's all.
I'll rest here for a bit,
then go and meet up with Naigus.
[Witch A]
Did you see that...?
It was the Grim Reaper.
[Witch B]
This place is done for.
[Witch C]
We need to flee.
It's a bunch of witches.
It doesn't seem like they
can see us here, though.
Take a closer look.
Their bodies are blurred.
It's just a hunch...
...but I think what we're
looking at is the past.
Maybe when the
explosion happened,
it sealed the events of that
day within the magnetic field...
And what we're seeing
is them played out again.
But I wonder...
...my dad showing up like
that and the
witches acting afraid...
Something feels off.
Was whatever happened
here really an accident?
What's wrong?
You see something?
That looked like--!
Yeah, no doubt about it.
That's Arachne.
[Guardian 1]
Lady Arachne...
Mosquito is waiting
for you at your carriage.
[Lady Arachne] And you
have Eibon's blueprints?
Yes... They're right here.
Eibon again!
[Lady Arachne laughs]
The first part's done.
We managed to
lure the Reaper here...
Now all we have to
do is blow up Brew
and this building
along with it.
What is going on here?
[Arachnid 5] The battle
for Brew continues.
The outcome is still uncertain.
We'll do whatever
we must to obtain it...
Among Eibon's creations,
Brew is the most important.
It is the acme
of his achievements...
It dwarfs any other Magic Tool.
Eight hundred years ago,
I designed a plan to
blow up Brew along with
the facility that held it
in order to prevent the Reaper
from ever learning
of the tool's existence.
But Brew is a masterpiece...
No one could hope to
destroy it with
a mere explosion.
It is far too powerful for that.
And now, after eight centuries,
Brew will not fall into
the hands of the witches.
Or the Grim Reaper
and his dear DWMA...
No... it will be mine.
♪ closing song ♪
[Lady Arachne] So, everybody,
what do you think...?
I realize you only got
a tiny peek at what
I was like eight
hundred years ago,
but that should be enough...
In those days,
I was busy setting traps,
killing witches, tricking Death,
making things explode...
Of course, I'm turning
over a new leaf now...
Perhaps I'll settle down
and open restaurant in a
quiet little village somewhere.
[Maka]
Who would believe that?
[Lady Arachne] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Mosquito's Storm...!
Ten Minutes to Fight
in the World of the Past?