A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
So, you've come.
Here you are...
it's about time.
Sorry to keep ya
waiting, Mifune.
Right, now let's do this thing.
One win one loss so far...
...this will be the
decisive battle.
That's right...
I'll show you who the
winner is once and for all.
Tsubaki...
you ready to go?
Yes.
Before you lies the
path of the demon...
...and the path of the warrior.
Tell me, Black Star...
Which of these two paths
are you going to follow?
♪ opening song ♪
I can't help but wonder
if handing over this
Magic Tool is the
right thing to do.
What is Dad planning...?
If he's after all these tools
for some sinister purpose...
I'll have to act.
Hey Kid, you should see this!
What, Patty?
There...
I wonder what it is?
Fools!
Warrior or Slaughterer...?
Showdown:
Mifune vs. Black Star?
Fools!
How does it look
out there, Azusa?
I hate to say it,
but not very good.
Our forces on the
front line are advancing,
but they've got a long way to go
before they reach the castle.
Fools!
And the relay stations...?
What's the situation there?
Well...
We've succeeded
in taking three of the six...
The stations in the
Middle East, Europe,
and Oceania are
under our control.
They are no longer
operational...
However...
The fight continues at
the other three stations.
Fools!
Destroying those
won't be enough...
We'd only delay the spread of
the madness, not stop it.
You're right about that.
Until we defeat
the Kishin itself...
...our victory
will be incomplete.
Fools!
Oh...
Lord Death.
Hmmm?
Fool!
It's Kid...
...he's returned.
And the Magic Tool?
He's succeeded in retrieving it.
Well...
...some good news, finally.
Tell him to find Joe
in the secret vault
and wait for further
instructions.
Hey, Kid, do you
recognize this place?
Yeah...
...the so-called contractor
is working in there.
This strange key and the
academy's recent secrecy...
I know they're hiding something.
And the answer...
...is behind this door.
In our earlier fights,
I thought I'd sensed
some potential in you...
I guess I was wrong about that.
Arrogant fool.
Underestimating me now
could be bad for your health...
Tsubaki!
Ninja Sword Mode!
Right!
Let's go...!
Speed Star!
Here I am!
He's fast!
Your soul resonance has
gotten faster than before...
I suppose you have improved
since the last time.
But are you fast enough?
Infinite Sword Style...
Get ready!
I see through your disguise.
The real one is...
There!
Sword Fang!
Horizontal Line attack!
One...
...two!
Third strike!
Are you okay?!
Pathetic...!
It's barely a scratch
You have sharp eyes...
Dodging kept you
alive this time.
I thought this would happen.
I have to use the
Enchanted Sword.
You did a great job, Kid...!
Thanks for taking on that
mission for your old man.
Hi there, cutie!
The Magic Tool please.
Here it is.
Before I hand it over...
I want to know everything
that's been going on.
What exactly does
this Magic Tool do?
...And why do you want it?
Oh... all right.
Eh?
Whoa!
Hold on a second!
You've been so secretive
and-and so dodgy!
And now you're going to tell
me just because I asked?!
What's going on here?
I don't understand!
Why would you do--
Sorry bout that...
But we really couldn't
let just anybody
know what we were doing...
It had to be a
secret operation...
You get it...?
We had to make sure our
plan was kept from
Arachne and the Kishin.
Oh really...?
So then we've been
suspicious for no reason?
We're pretty stupid, huh?
But now...
...we've got the Magic
Tool in our hands...
...so we can afford
to be a bit more open.
Okay... so tell
me what it does, then.
This little guy...
...was Eibon's final creation...
You see...
Eibon, is the last Magic Tool.
Well...
plan says we go in there.
But what do we do...?
Just march right in?
I don't know...
Our orders were simply to
infiltrate the castle.
And so we will.
These should make
it a bit easier.
Advaaance!
The castle isn't far now!
Let's move!
Advaaance!
Damn DWMA!
They're doing
better than I thought.
Mosquito...
What is taking you so long?
Forgive me, my lady...
...it's a tougher fight
than expected.
All right then...
...time for the secret weapon.
Are you sure about this,
Lady Arachne...?
Ou--Our own soldiers
are still within range!
Do it anyway.
As you wish.
And so...
...it comes to this
in the end, does it?
A new weapon...
One that fires a
compressed version
of the Kishin's
madness wavelength.
One shot from this should be all
we need to win the day.
This weapon will
decimate the enemy...
...and anything
else in its path.
Prepare yourselves
for utter devastation.
What's that?
Now, while he's distracted...
Tsubaki...
Enchanted Sword Mode!
Got it!
With the sorry state you're in,
you won't last much longer.
Don't worry...
I plan on making this quick.
Let's go.
Soul Resonance!
Shadow Star!
Such anger and malice...
Is it the path of
the demon then?
I'll defeat you...
nothing else matters to me.
Think hard before you say that.
You still have a chance
to choose the right path.
Shut up...!
I don't need advice from you!
Those eyes...
They look familiar.
What the hell's that?!
What do you know...?
No one ever told me
the castle could move!
It's been a long time...
...Great Wizard Eibon.
'It's been a long time'?
That means...
Dad and Eibon
do know each other.
Yes, Lord Death.
Sorry, but we don't
have time to catch up...
I want you to lend
me Brew's power.
Why do you need Brew?
Well...
...thanks to the Kishin
and that spider witch...
...we're in a bit of a pickle.
Asura and Arachne?
Father.
Tell me how you and
Eibon know each other.
That's a good question.
I guess it might be helpful if
I explained some of our history.
It's been a long time...
...but Eibon and I used
to fight side by side.
He was a member of
my elite guard squadron...
He knew the
Kishin, Asura, well...
It's hard to believe now...
but they were comrades once.
If he was one of yours...
...then why did he
create the Magic Tools?
Hmmm...
Well, there was a lot
going on back then.
What a great explanation.
Thank you.
How should I put it...?
Well, he always loved
playing with machines...
Yes.
Very helpful.
Ah, jeez...!
Well...
His original goal
was to preserve
and protect order
in the world...
...that's why he began
his research into Magic Tools.
Obviously, for any object of
great power, there are always
those who are willing to risk
anything to obtain that power.
And, of course, the more
powerful the object is...
...the greater the danger of it
falling into the wrong hands.
Eibon knew all this,
but he had faith in humanity...
...so he continued his
research nonetheless.
Eventually...
...his work took on
a more narrow focus...
He began studying
one area exclusively.
It became an obsession.
What area was that?
Immortality.
Hello, weird guy!
Huh!
What kind of greeting is that?
No...!
What's Excalibur doing here?!
Fool!
Why wouldn't I be here?
Him again?!
Ooh, the funny alien guy!
This should be interesting!
It was not idle
curiosity that led
to Eibon's immortality
research.
Indeed...
the true reason...
...is much more tragic.
His wife lay dying...
Eibon's obsession with
immortality was born
because he desperately
sought to save his beloved.
But no matter how great
the inventor or how noble
the cause, transcending death
is an impossible feat.
Not even Eibon could hope to
succeed in such an endeavor.
But when all seemed lost,
someone appeared by his side,
offering help and
comforting words...
That someone was...
...the witch Arachne!
Come on.
Is this guy for real?!
I can't be sure...!
It's a heart-rending tale...!
But what if it's nothing
but another manipulation?!
I assure you, it's not.
Eibon and Arachne
joined forces...
They combined his
research into immortality
with her research
on Magic Weapons.
And from that...
...the Magic Tool Brew
came into being.
Long ago...
I met a man whose eyes looked
exactly like yours do now.
He bore the same
star tattoo as well.
He showed no mercy,
even to those who deserved it.
You...
...you're Star Clan...
You're close to forsaking
the path of the warrior
for the path of the demon.
Oh, please...
What use do I have for paths...?
I'm here to win,
plain and simple...
That's all that matters.
It's not too late.
Stop while you can.
That's enough...
I'm done listening.
Yeah, that's a great
story, samurai...
...but why should I care
about some dumb clan
that got itself wiped out?
Because the child of a
demon is a demon as well...
Your path has
been decided for you.
Shut up!
You have the strength
to be so much more...
So why this?
There's nothing greater
in this life than winning...
Victory's always
the path I choose.
You're wielding a
double edged sword...
It may kill your opponents, but
it's cutting your soul as well.
White Star...
He was the first man
I ever truly feared.
But, feared as he was, he was
not fearless himself.
The thought that he might
one day be defeated
made him tremble... it shook him
to the very depths of his soul.
Man...
...for a samurai,
you sure talk a lot!
You're different, though...
You've already tasted
defeat, haven't you?
What did you say?!
He strayed from the
path for a reason.
Perhaps you should hear it
before you decide.
All right, White Star...
...let's end this.
Your eyes...!
You aren't even
human anymore, are you?
He couldn't conquer the
darkness inside himself...
What about you?
Will you fight that darkness, or
will you become a demon too?
I'm not gonna lose!
He was defeated
because he was weak!
I'll show you...!
I'm stronger than him!
You foolish boy.
He wasn't weak!
No matter what, he always had
to push harder, reach higher...
He never knew when to stop...
...because of that...
He lost himself...
...the warrior became a demon.
I'll ask you again.
Which path will you follow...?
That of the warrior...
or of the demon?
Shut up, samurai...
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You're nothing but a fool if you
think you can order me around.
You've chosen the demon.
I can do nothing more for you.
Black Star!!!
How delicious this power is...
Reduce them to lumps of flesh.
You have a habit of popping up
at unexpected times, Exaclibur.
Why are you here now?
Did you come to see Eibon?
Hah...!
That's just a bonus.
My reason goes a great deal
deeper than that.
Oh...! You're here to
help us out, then?
Fool!
That isn't it.
I've come to observe.
Now...
let's begin.
Brew...
Unlock.
♪ closing song ♪
Energy coefficient stable...
Soul detection radar in
high altitude mode...
Weapons locked and loaded...
All system lights are green...
Lord Death, we're ready!
Good.
Death City Robot: Fight Mode.
Transform!
Ta-dah!!
Well, that was a
fun game, Azusa...
But does this thing
actually transform?
Of course it doesn't!
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Miraculous
Coffee Table Flip...
Fly, Our Death City Robot?
I told you it doesn't transform.
Oh really?