[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[explosion]
A bomb, huh?
Over there... look-it!
[Kid] They're arranged
at random...
...without any symmetry.
Absolutely disgusting!
[Free]
I heard an explosion.
[Eruka] It must be one of
the Tadpole Bombs I set.
We need to hurry.
I smell something.
Yes...
We're almost there now...
The Kishin is just ahead.
[Maka laughing insanely]
You fools I'm the
one who's leading.
Things are going to
get interesting now.
♪ opening song ♪
It's an abomination.
Such an inconsistent
arrangement is unconscionable...
Damn it.
[Liz]
Hey Kid...
...let's forget about
consistency for now.
We can pass right on through...
Just don't look
at them for too long.
[Kid] Oh, it's starting
to make me sick.
I don't feel good.
[Liz]
See, what did I tell you?
Okay...In your defense,
I suppose poorly arranged
bombs are as terrifying
to you as a path
full of monsters
would be to most normal people.
You know,
it might not just be the
whole inconsistent
arrangement thingy...
Those are bombs, after all...
Who wouldn't be scared?
Yeah... it's possible
you've got a point there.
[Kid] This trap may be
the end of me...
It's over.
[Liz]
Whoa! Hold on just a sec!
The Kishin's gonna wake
back up if you
give up this easily.
You're a Reaper!
If you can't do this,
then who can?!
You can say
whatever you want...
I'm nothing but
filthy Reaper scum...
Just put me by the
curb on garbage day.
It's your turn, Patty...
Tell him in that special
way that you have.
Okay.
Get yer ass moving
now, damn you!
[Kid whimpers]
[explosions]
[Kid yelling]
[Liz] Nice... he's
using the blasts
to give himself more momentum.
[Patty giggles]
Well done...
You did an incredible job
of finally getting his
butt moving Patty...
Amazing!
Yeah, I was really scary,
wasn't I sis?
Damn it, Patty!
I hate you so much!
I really, really hate you!
Hang in there.
It's just going to be
just a little bit longer.
Something's following us
at breakneck speed,
and it's catching up.
Free, we've gotta inject
the black blood
into the Kishin...
If anything happens to
this case before we do,
then Medusa is going
to slaughter us both!
I know she will,
but I've got an idea.
Let me borrow that
tadpole you're riding on.
I'm gonna need it.
Huh...? Tadpole Jackson?
What are you gonna do with him?
Not much...
...just get a jump on the enemy.
[Maka]
May My Soul Reach You...
A Dry Heart Inside
Unbearable Isolation?
[Maka giggles insanely]
Let's go!
It's all just...
...so funny, you know?
Quit it... Please stop...
You're all wobbly
and giggly. I don't like it...
Stay away from me.
I told you...
I hate wobbly giggles!
That's too bad. I like 'em.
Hey. It's black.
It's so pretty.
What's with this...?
She's really lost it now.
[Maka] Go on,
hurt me some more...
You can do better
than this, can't you?
[Maka laughs madly]
So this is... madness?
It protects your partner
from feeling any fear.
Her soul and her opponent's
soul are irrelevant...
They have nothing
to do with this fight.
Come on...
Gimme something new...
Can't you do anything like
eye gouging or fish hooking...
No? Well maybe you'd
like to tear off my tongue?
What're you doing
out there, Maka...?
Getting your tongue torn off
was not part of
the plan, remember?!
Damn it...
Now I'm getting pulled
into the madness, too...
Hurry, Maka...!
Or you won't ever
be able to come back!
[Maka]
Soul...
Oh wow...
That's embarrassing.
[Soul] It's not that different
from how you normally are.
Now hurry up and do
whatever you need to do.
[Maka]
Yeah...
I'm working on it.
I think I can do this.
I had a weird kind of
premonition when I was sane.
Now that I've got the
same madness as Crona,
I can match our soul wavelengths
and find out what it is.
Feel it...
[Maka]
Look at this.
This is my soul...
It really is pretty tiny.
Another one.
It's not in the best shape...
...a little twisted...
...a bit worse for the wear...
...kinda rough
around the edges, too.
But it's always there for me...
This is my Soul Eater's soul.
Now, where's Crona's soul?
That must be
his soul up there.
It's hard to explain,
but I'm sensing a
very, dry wavelength.
[Maka]
A desert...?
It almost looks
like it could be a beach.
But with no ocean.
Crona?
[explosions]
[Blair] I'm gonna
make you pay for this.
He was my food slave.
Pum... pumpkin... pumpkin!
Smashing Pumpkin!
[Mizune cry out]
[explosion]
Would you like some more?
It's important for a lady
to be limber and flexible.
Five against one and there's not
a scratch on my perfect body.
They could use some practice.
Chi-chi-chi, chi-chi-chi...
[Mizune begin to chant]
Chi-chi-chi...
I wouldn't get too cocky
if I were you, little kitty...
Don't you know that the
cornered rat'll bite the cat?
Hot...! Hot...! Hot...! Hot!
Do you think I'm going
to let you get away with
trying to seduce men on my turf?
Oh...! Oh! Oh!
Oh no...! I can't take any more!
You're gonna be
one dead feline.
Big talk coming from a
quintuple-decker mousey.
What a distasteful outfit.
Like you're really one to talk.
Isn't this top a little drafty?
Hot!
Didn't you die or something?
[Medusa] At long last the
black blood is ready.
All that remains now
is to inject it into the
Kishin and revive it...
You can keep struggling
as long as you want,
but it's no use...
My plan is going to
succeed, no matter what.
[Stein]
Tell me...
If you do get your way,
and the Kishin is revived,
what will happen to
the Demon Sword child?
Your black blood
research is complete...
You're done with
the experiment for which
you needed this child.
So now...?
Oh, please...
What am I going
to do with it...?
Let's see, I ordered it around
all its life, so now it's
lacking in independence...
One reason not to be an
overbearing mother I suppose...
Anyway, Crona
didn't turn out well.
It was failure of mine.
Lacking independence
or not, he's your kid...
What are you going
to do with him?
What will you
do with your child?
[Medusa laughs]
Quit laughing!
What's got you
two so irritated...
You sound ridiculous.
Do I really have to tell you
what you already know...?
Think about it this way...
...why would I keep something
that I no longer need...?
It makes much more
sense to throw it away...
But why do you ask...?
Do you want it?
You can have my
hand-me-downs if you like.
You could use it for your
experiments or something.
You evil wi--.
You damn witch!
Yes, what is it?
You...Why, you...!
That all...?
If you want to
talk about something...
...the least you can do is
know what you're going to say!
Spirit...! Watch it...!
You shouldn't be so reckless.
Oh great...
Don't snivel
like a little baby...
You're a grown man.
I know that, damn it...
But unlike you,
Stein, I am a parent...
So to me this is...
...how do I explain
it to you...?
It's unforgivable!
If a child's own
mother abandons him,
who else in the world
will he be able to turn to?
Yes! Exactly!
That's what I've been
trying to say all along.
[Death Scythe]
In any case...
...we're definitely
going to defeat her!
[Stein] That's pretty much been
the plan this whole time.
What should I do
now that I'm here?
Right here...
This is my area.
I'm drawing the line to mark it.
But what should I do now?
Kicking up sand doesn't
seem to do me any good...
and there's not much else
besides sand in this place.
Even the sun is lifeless...
It's just hanging
there asleep in the sky.
Doing nothing is
probably the best plan.
[Shadow Crona]
Hey.
My name is Crona.
[Young Crona thinks]
Of course...
It always shows up
when I'm doing nothing.
[Shadow Crona]
Can I ask you some questions?
Here goes.
[Young Crona] And here we go
with the questions again,
when all I really
want to do is nothing.
Can I pass if I want?
[Shadow Crona]
That's up to you I guess.
Here are my questions.
First question...
what's your name?
I pass.
That was an easy one.
You mean you won't
even say what your name is?
Why do you think that is?
I pass.
Here let me see if I can
answer that one for you...
Basically, you can't answer
other people's questions,
so you question yourself in
order to keep
your mind intact...
Sound about right?