[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[bells toll]
[glass shatters]
[Soul]
Evil Monk Rasputin...
You're mine!
I'm gonna eat your soul!
[Rasputin]
You can try.
But your effort
will be wasted...
Not even bullets can do
any harm to me.
Guess it's a good thing
I don't use bullets, then.
I hate wasted effort.
So like I said...
this Kishin egg soul of yours
is about to be my dinner.
Ahh...
[alarm clock clanging]
Souls are so yummy...
I hope it's a cool morning.
That's how cool days
always start out.
[Soul] And a cool
guy like me deserves
the coolest morning possible.
Morning, Soul.
It's time for you
to get up, sleepy boy.
B-B-Blair!
But there's no
real hurry, right?
[eggs sizzling]
[Maka]
There we go... all done!
[Blair] You could stay here
and play with me today...
We'll have some fun...
[door knob being turned]
Soul... Drag yourself out of
bed and eat some breakfast...
It's almost time for school.
Oh, good morning Maka.
[rooster crows]
[Soul thinks]
I have a feeling...
That this particular morning...
[Maka]
Soul... You jerk!
[Soul thinks]
Is not gonna be cool at all.
♪ opening song ♪
[Student A] How many
souls did you collect?
[Student B] Twelve.
How many did you get?
So, Maka...
[Maka]
Quiet please...
Can't you see
that I'm reading...?
Don't interrupt me.
I don't get what
you're so mad about...
It's just a stupid book.
Maka... chop!
Was there something,
you wanted to say?
[Soul] It's about this rumor
that's been goin' around...
You know that one
teacher we used to have--
The one who died...
They found him with a
statue of Liberty sticking
out of his brain...
[Maka] Oh, you mean
Sid and the
"Statue-to the-forehead
incident...
What about it?
[Soul]
You haven't heard?
They say there's some
weird dude that's been comin'
after students from
the academy lately...
I guess some kid in the
next class over got messed
up pretty bad...
The point is--
everyone who's seen this dude,
they all say the same thing...
They say he was a zombie
who had a hole in the
middle of his forehead!
[Maka cries out]
[Soul] Did you really
have to hit me again?
[Maka] So your theory is
that the zombie is Sid...?
Please, it's only a story
somebody made up
to scare everyone.
[Death Scythe] All right,
kids... ...quiet down...
Class is about to start.
[Death Scythe] I'm not going to
bother taking attendance...
But I will tell you
one thing right now.
Anyone who thinks the
bell decides
when class is over...
...is wrong... I do... clear?
[Death Scythe thinks]
How was that, Maka...?
Isn't your old man cool?
[Soul]
Hey...
Is it just me,
or is that stupid father
of yours makin' that
goofy face right at us?
[Maka] Um...
I think it's just you.
And please do not
refer to him as my father.
What's up with this,
Death Scythe...?
Are you supposed to be
our new teacher
now or something?
I'm just a substitute...
until they find someone
who can fill Sid's
position permanently.
But that still means
I'm in charge of this class...
So as long as I'm here,
you will call me
Professor Death Scythe!
Alright then,
let's take attendance.
You said you
weren't gonna take roll!
I'm not going to take
attendance for the guys...
but I think I will
for all the ladies.
Dammit! Quit bein' a creep!
Oh please.
He doesn't know
when to quit, this one...
Soul Eater... Soul Eater...
Here it is.
For today...
...you get the lowest
grade possible.
Okay...
let's get this
class started now.
[Soul]
Hey, old man,
what did you just
write down there?
Oh, that reminds me...
Maka and Soul...
[Soul]
What is it now?
[Death Scythe] Lord Death wants
to see you in the Death Room...
You've been excused
from class, so get going.
(shoo shoo)...
He wants to see us?
[Maka]
Engage the Witch Hunter!
~A Remedial Lesson
in the Graveyard?~
[knock on door]
[Maka]
Hello!
I wonder why Lord Death
wants to see us.
Who knows?
[Black Star] Look at Soul
and Maka down there...
They think they can show
their backs to me, do they?
Tsubaki... let's go.
Right.
[Black Star] Assassin's
Rule Number One!
Dissolve in the darkness
and erase your breath...
Wait for an opening
to attack your target.
[Maka] Oh look...
it's Black Star.
[Soul] Why're you standing up
there yelling like an idiot?
They found us pretty easily.
It can be real difficult to
hide when you're as
big a star as I am.
Oh well... That's a disadvantage
I think I can handle...
Pretty big of me, huh, Tsubaki?
Oh, yes.
[Maka]
Seriously?
[Soul] What are
you doing here...?
Were you guys called
in to see Lord Death, too?
[Black Star]
What if we were?
[Maka]
Here, I'll call him.
"Forty-two, Forty-two,
Five-sixty-four: whenever you
wanna knock on Death's door."
[bells ding]
[Maka]
Lord Death, are you there?
[Death]
Ya, ya!
Hi! Hello! What's up...?
Thanks for coming.
Scythe Meister Maka
reporting in.
Yeah, and Dark Arm
Meister Black Star, too.
And Tsubaki. I'm his partner.
Well... what did
you want with us?
[Death] Right... I have
a little assignment
for you guys to take on.
[All]
Assignment?
[Death]
Some extra lessons.
[Maka] Huh?! Those extra lessons
that stupid people get?
Those lessons?!
Well screw that...
I'm gonna be a Death Scythe...
I'm way too cool
for extra lessons.
[Death] Do you remember your
duty as meisters and weapons?
Yes... Our duty as meisters
is to feed our
weapons 99 Kishin souls
and one witch's soul...
We collect evil souls in
order to keep
the world at peace...
We work to
create a Death Scythe...
...weapon of the
Grim Reaper, Death.
[Death]
You are absolutely right!
But do you know how
many souls all of you
have managed to collect?
Exactly zero!
[Death] It isn't something to
laugh about, Chuckles...
Anyway, are you ready to
learn what your extra
lessons will entail...?
Maybe you've already
heard the rumors.
About Sid...
Who taught here at the
academy until recently...
[Soul]
See...? I was right...
It wasn't just a story.
Yeah... But a zombie?
I always thought he was
a really good teacher.
[Death]
You're right...
When he was alive,
he was regarded as an
excellent teacher...
But when he became
a zombie, he changed...
He has been released
from the fear of death...
...and now he wants others to
have the same freedom he does.
He is trying to train students
to free themselves as well,
but when a student
won't listen, Sid attacks.
Another difficulty is that
we still don't know who
changed Sid into a zombie...
or what their motive
could possibly have been.
Okay...! You can leave
it all to me sir!
For our extra lesson,
we just have to
eliminate these guys?
[Death] Yup,
that's pretty much it.
Now, I don't want to
put too much pressure on you...
but if you happen to
fail at these extra lessons.
Then you're all
going to be expelled.
[All]
What...?!
You're gonna kick us out?!
There's nothin'
to worry about...
I can take care of guys
like this in my sleep.
Come out...!
Nap time's over, zombie!
[Black Star] Hey, Tsubaki...
this is Sid's grave, isn't it?
Sure this is where we
want to start looking...?
Don't zombies get up
and move around a lot?
Might as well check this
place first to be
sure he isn't here.
I'm not gonna let myself
get expelled over some
walking dead guy.
It looks like an ordinary
grave stone to me.
[Soul] I never even listened
to your lessons. So there!
Soul seems...
a bit disturbed.
[Maka] I always thought
I was a great scythe meister
like my mother was...
How can I suddenly
be expelled?
What's up with Maka?
She seems kinda down.
Black Star, aren't you at least
a little worried about all this?
Where the hell are you hiding?!
Hey Soul, why don't we
go piss on Sid's grave?
What d'ya think about that?
Yeah, and while we're at it,
why don't we take
a dump on it too?
--Come on, Zombie!
--Get out here!
We're gonna
beat you to a pulp!
You're just afraid to fight me
'cause I'm bigger than you.
--What? Are you too
scared to fight us?
You're hiding cause you're
a little coward, I know it.
Everybody knows it!
I think you can stop now...
Maka!
Are you scared, girl?
[Sid]
I think you are.
That's what Sid's become?
[Soul]
Guess so.
[Sid]
Maka... Soul...
Black Star... Tsubaki...
Good morning.
Good afternoon. Good night.
How have you been and all that?
I always tried to
remember my manners.
That's the kind of man I was.
Tsubaki, let's get ready
to end this guy.
Right.
[Death]
And so it begins.
[Maka] Tell me Sid...
why are you doing this?
Ding... dong...
dong... ding...
Being a zombie's amazing...
there are so many more
things I can get away with now.
Class is in session...
I always was a man to
start class right
with the bell...
Punctuality is important.
[Black Star]
This'll be fun.
I get to teach you
a lesson now, teacher...
And since it's
coming from me,
you know it'll be a big one!
[Soul] We don't want
to be expelled...
so we'll take your extra lesson.
But I gotta say,
I don't know what we're
gonna learn from a
decaying piece of flesh.
If you become a zombie...
...then death no longer
looms over you...
You can escape from
fear and be free.
That's wrong and
you know it...
You were never the type
of man who would say that!
You'll understand
when you're dead!
Black Star!
There'll be no need to
thank me for the lesson...
It's on the house.
I never was the
kind of man...
to hold back!
[Sid] I'd recommend
you just give up...
You one-star meisters don't
have a chance of beating me.
I'm hungry.
Can we just get his damn
zombie soul already?
Sid's right.
He is very strong.
One star meisters like us
can't compete with him...
When he was alive,
he was designated a
three star meister.
[Soul]
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Hey, Sid...! If you keep
swinging your tombstone
around like that,
you might bang it into
your fat head and die again.
[Sid]
It's my tombstone...
I can use it
however I want, can't I?
Now then, kids...
It's time for second period.
Ding... dong...
dong... ding...
Oh, yeah, I forgot to mention:
when this lesson is over...
You're all gonna die.
Then I guess we'll be
cutting class today...
...think I'll go home and
take a nice, hot bath...
[duck quacking]
This is so boring.
[Blair] Maybe I should
take some classes, too.
I bet Maka and Soul are
having lots of fun right now.
[Sid]
What's wrong?
Why aren't you
working together?
You have to establish a
connection between the
souls of weapon and meister.
[Black Star] You're giving
advice to the enemy?!
I've always been
an enthusiastic educator.
[Sid] That's the kind
of man I was!
And now I'll
teach you how to die.
The Living End!
[explosion]
Black Star!
[Maka thinks] Sid was
a knife-meister...
But even without his blade,
the way he fights,
that tombstone
is all he needs...
So this...
...is a three star meister.
Ding... dong...
Dong... ding...
Looks like class is over.
Ready to die yet, girl?
Well, what do you say...?
Aren't you afraid of dying?
If you become a zombie
then you'll be free from
that fear of death forever.
[Black Star]
My head is killing me...
Your preaching is starting to
give me a headache,
you damn zombie.
I'm not listening to
any lesson of yours...
It doesn't matter
what you say...
Who's gonna pay attention
to a rotting corpse like you...
As long as there's
a big star like me around!
Being a three-star
meister doesn't matter.
I am...
...Black... Star!
[Sid thinks] He aimed for
the solar plexus,
the weakest point in
the center of the body.
[Death]
That was a nice attack...
As one would expect from a
dark assassin like Black Star.
[Black Star]
Tsubaki-- Shuriken Mode!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
You can't run away!
As if I'd even try!
[Soul]
Maka... He's coming.
The Living... End!
[explosion]
[Sid laughs]
What the--
[Sid thinks] She avoided it with
such a narrow margin for error.
People need fear to survive.
We experience it so
that we can grow stronger!
[Death]
Hmm?
If she wasn't afraid
in this situation I'd
call that reckless...
But Maka has the courage
to fight in spite of her fear...
[Soul]
Maka.
Let's do what he said...
See if you can match
my soul's wavelength.
But that hasn't worked
for us a single time before.
So what...
This is us. We can do it.
Let's go! Soul Resonance!
[Maka and Soul power up]
The legendary super skill
of the scythe meister!
Witch Hunter!
[Maka]
No!!
You trying to kill us...?
What the hell, Maka?!
Nice...!
This is all your fault...!
Do it right, idiot!
[Soul] What? You've
gotta be kidding me!
Why is this my fault...?!
You're the idiot here,
getting mad at me for nothing...
Die!
[Maka] Die?!
How can you say that?!
--[Maka] You die!
--That was incredible power.
[Soul]
Cry baby!
I wanted to do it
without a super skill.
I just wanted to do
things the simple way!
[Maka]
Huh?
He's gone.
[Soul] No...
he's hiding underground.
[Maka]
He's down there?
[Sid yells out]
[Soul] Damn...! He dodged
our attack again!
Now, Black Star.
[Black Star]
Yeah... I got it.
What Sid's doing now
is using the first of
the assassin's rules.
[Tsubaki] Dissolve in the
darkness and erase your breath.
Wait for an opening
to attack your target.
[Black Star]
Tsubaki.
Let's get a step
ahead of this guy.
[Tsubaki]
Right.
[Black Star]
You zombie bastard...
You're not going to upstage
me in this performance.
[Maka thinks] Black
Star's movements
seem different from usual.
[Black Star thinks] Only one man
is gonna die in this graveyard.
And it's not gonna be me.
[Black Star]
Trap Star.
Assassin's Rule Number Two:
Concentrate on the target...
If I listen carefully,
I can hear his
soul's wavelength.
I can pick it
up through Tsubaki.
[Maka thinks] His
breathing stopped.
[Death]
And now...
[Black Star]
Trap Star activate!
I think that it's about time
to send you back to the grave...
You really stink.
What are you doing,
tying me up along
with this guy?!
I wouldn't have to if
you didn't get in my way.
--[Soul] Hey, let us outta here.
--[Death] So far so good...
Maybe it's time to
take a break from this.
[Kid] So now they just have
to find the person who turned
Sid into a zombie, right?
[Death]
That's right.
Who's responsible...?
Do you know?
He's no ordinary enemy, is he?
[Death] You're familiar with
my current weapon, right...?
Death Scythe...?
And I assume that you have
at least heard of the
meister who trained him.
[Kid]
Yeah...
It was Maka's
mother, wasn't it...?
What about her?
[Death] Actually...
that's not quite right...
Maka's mother was
Death Scythe's second partner...
He had another.
So that means...
This person was his first?
[Death] Yes. The man behind
this is Dr. Franken Stein.
And not only was he
Death Scythe's first partner...
He was also unquestionably
the greatest meister to ever
graduate from the academy.
[Stein] Can't seem to get
my head on straight.
I give up.
Too tired.
He's here.
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] In the dead of night,
when even the plants are asleep,
a cry echoes out in
a patchwork laboratory...
[Tsubaki] Fear.
Shrieks. Splatter.
The horror that appeared
before these innocent young
boys and girls was Franken--
[Maka] Whoa,
whoa, wait, Tsubaki!
You gotta build the
mood a little more!
[Tsubaki] Sorry. I guess
I'm not very good
at this sort of thing...
[Maka]
Sure you are.
C'mon, just give it a try...
[Tsubaki]
"oooo! I curse you!"
[Maka]
That was good...
[Tsubaki] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Shape of the Soul
~Enter the Ultimate
Meister, Stein?~
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!