[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
Yea...! Yea...! Yea!
It's done, Lord Death...
We have officially
accomplished our mission.
Well done, Maka.
You have successfully
collected ninety-nine Kishin
souls and the
soul of one witch...
Congratulations...
As promised, I will make
Soul my personal weapon.
You'll finally be a Deathscythe.
Yeah...
Hey... What are you doing
down there on the floor...
You're gonna be late for school.
♪ opening song ♪
All right people,
as I'm sure you know...
there isn't much time remaining.
In three short days,
you'll all be taking the
general test for meisters and
weapons, the Super
Written Exam.
I assume you have
all been studying for it.
[Maka thinks] Of course...!
I've been cramming for
this for a month now.
Just to warn you,
I wrote the test
questions this year.
If you've studied the materials,
you should be fine.
If not, you may
have a problem.
In either case, good luck.
Kay! Class is dismissed!
Ugh... yuck...
There's gotta be
some short-cut way
to memorize everything.
You don't learn by
taking short cuts, Soul...
and I'm not gonna let you
get away with cheating, either.
[Harvar] Think you'll get top
score again this year, Ox?
Well... we'll see.
[Maka thinks]
Yeah... Last year,
I would've had the highest
score if it wasn't for Ox.
There are a couple of
hard workers in this class
who could beat out my score...
Like her...
Last year Maka came in second...
right behind me.
Yo, Black Star,
do you know why they
call this test the
Super Written Exam?
It's because supposedly
whoever comes in first
is destined to make
a Death Scythe.
What, seriously!?
[Maka] That's right.
It's my destiny...
Mama was at the
top of her year too...
I have to come in first...
It's in my blood.
It's settled! I'm gonna get
first and turn you into
a Death Scythe, Tsubaki.
Okay!
Way cool! This is our
first written exam ever!
Let's go!
Just because they put the
word 'super' in front of it
doesn't mean I'm going to study.
You sound pretty confident.
You aren't going to
prepare for it at all?
I am a reaper.
I've got a pretty good
grasp of phasmology.
[Maka] I forgot...
I'll have to compete
against Kid this year too.
This could get real ugly.
What on earth
are you doing, Spirit?
I'm sending positive energy to
Maka so she'll do
well on the test.
O, kay...
Anything else?
[Stein]
No, continue.
Yeah! Maka!
[Maka]
The Super Written Exam...
Heart-pounding, Reeling,
and Restless, You're Kidding?
'Kay...! It's time to study!
Hey, so Maka...are tests
like this a lot of fun to take?
Uh-huh...
You get to find out how
much you've learned so far...
You can tell from your
score and class ranking
It's kinda like
a game, almost...
But I have to study
extra hard this time...
They say that whoever
gets the top score will
create a Death Scythe.
From what I hear it's
really difficult to
become a Death Scythe...
Your Papa must be amazing, Maka.
It's my mom who's amazing.
She managed to make
my good-for-nothing
Papa into a Death Scythe.
[Soul]
Okay, so the study of
phasmology
began with, who again?
Oh, you're studying for
this Super Written
test-thingy too, Soul?
Yeah. I'm a little busy here...
Leave me alone.
That's no fun...
I'm bored...! Play with me!
I'll kill her.
[Black Star] Four hundred
and ninety-eight...
Four hundred and ninety-nine...
Five hundred.
The next time
I get one wrong,
it's gonna be a
thousand sit-ups.
'Kay, let's see...
What's this say?
[Soul]
Dammit!
Let's quit with the penalty
exercises and just study...
--I'll help you!
--four... five...
[Liz] Smart girl
transformation complete.
Let's study.
You look so smart, Sis!
Yeah...
Oh my... so you
two were serious
about hitting the books, huh?
If you guys need
help with anything--
Um...
That doesn't look like studying.
It's break time right now.
I've got this one hair
that's longer than the others.
I can't concentrate
because it's bothering me.
Idiot! What do you
think you're doing...?!
Eyebrow grooming is to
be left up to me!
What happens if the left
and right sides are uneven?!
Kid, do you remember
how long it took the
last time I let you
pluck them for me...?
It was a month!
Fine then, I promise to
do it quicker this time.
Please...! I beg you...!
Huh...? Huh?
If you're going to
keep begging me...
Yes!
[Kid]
First we need a blueprint.
Go somewhere else.
We're trying to study.
What concept should I go for...?
Strong and yet subtle, maybe?
Yes, that's perfect.
You need to get over it, Kid.
They're just eyebrows.
Maka, Maka, Maka...
Maka, Maka...etc...
[Blair cries out]
Why won't anybody
play with me...?
That test must be
a really big deal.
A relaxing bath...
Just what I needed.
I'm so proud of Black Star
for studying this hard.
I never thought
I'd see the day.
I'll make some dinner
to reward him.
[Black Star]
Yahoo!
Crap, that was loud!
I have to be quiet
Very quiet.
No more studying for me...
That stuff's way too boring.
I'll just steal the test
like any good assassin would do.
There they are!
[Black Star laughs]
With this there's
no way I'll fail.
Mine'll be the biggest
score in the whole class!
[Black Star screams]
[Tsubaki]
Black Star?
Where are you?
How's the studying going?
I told you, we're on a break.
You've been on
break for three days now!
My nails weren't painted.
It was bothering me.
[Soul]
All done.
I'm finished.
I've done all
that I can tonight...
Now it's time to
rest up for tomorrow.
My little girl will get
first place tomorrow.
She will. She will.
She will. She will...
Maka. Maka. Maka.
She will. She will.
Maka will get first
place tomorrow!
Maka. Maka. Maka.
I will do my best tomorrow...
I'm ready!
[Blair cheers]
I'll be proctoring
your exam today...
just one more thing
before we get started...
Ya... hoo...
It's Black Star!
A certain idiot decided
to sneak into Professor Stein's
laboratory last night
to steal the exam.
Ya... hoo...
So... don't be an
idiot like this guy.
You'll have sixty minutes.
Keep your eyes
on your own paper.
La la la la...
Start writing!
[Maka thinks] You're fine...
just relax.
[Soul thinks] Anyone who spends
all that time studying to
do this honestly is a chump...
I prefer to work
smart instead of hard...
That's why I look for shortcuts.
The highest score on
this test wins no matter what,
so who cares how you get it.
My entire body is
covered in cheat sheets.
How's this for a shortcut Maka?
I'm gonna ace this thing,
no problem.
You sure this
everything you have?
Why...? You wanna take
my underwear, too?!
[Maka thinks]
What an idiot.
[Sid]
Go back to your seat...
But this is the only other
chance you're gonna get.
Yeah, yeah.
[classmates laugh]
[Maka thinks] No, I need to
concentrate on my test.
Looks like the next
few are fill-in-the-blank.
Let's see...
"Complete the following
sentences as
accurately as you can"...
One: A sound soul...
Easy...!
Dwells within a... sound...
[Liz] Okay. A sound soul
dwells within sound skin
and sound cuticles.
[Liz thinks] That
doesn't sound right.
[Soul thinks]
I hadn't even answered
a single question yet...
This is the opposite of cool.
Wait...!
Maybe I'm not done for...
The brilliant Kid is
sitting right next to me!
Awful!
[Kid cries out]
[Kid]
It's not neat enough.
[Soul thinks] The freak's
still writing his name...!
He's useless.
And here?
She's writing with a crayon?!
[Soul] She's worn down
the yellow quite a lot.
[Patty laughs and sings]
Giraffe...! Giraffe!
I love Giraffes...
[Soul]
Of course. A giraffe.
[Maka] "Answer this
question true or false."
Uh-huh! It's just
like Professor Stein
to throw in a trick
question to trip us up.
[Tsubaki thinks]
Is this a trick...?
No, it couldn't be...
Professor Stein wouldn't do
anything to trick his students.
[Maka thinks]
False!
You can't fool me with
that little trick, Professor!
[Ox]
Excuse me, Sid...
I'm all finished.
[Sid] Just read a
book or something.
[Liz]
Know it all brat.
Ten minutes remaining.
[Soul thinks] What!...?
I'm running out of time!
And Kid's still
trying to write his name.
[Patty]
All done!
What!?
Woo-hoo! It's so pretty!
[Soul thinks] She made
her test into a giraffe.
Better watch out...!
I can break your neck!
[Soul thinks]
That's pretty good.
Damn... it's awful.
Just... awful!
No matter what I do,
I can't get the 'k' right.
I'm useless garbage!
I'm a horrible, disgusting
person who doesn't
deserve to live another day.
Uh Sid... Kid just collapsed.
Let him be.
[Black Star]
Soul...
[Soul thinks]
Black Star!
You're writing... In blood?
That's right... You saw
the answers in the laboratory...
...and now you're
trying to give them to me.
I'll carry out
your dying wish...
I promise I will!
What good is
your stupid autograph?!
You choose: be quiet or die...
Test is almost over!
[Maka thinks] All right.
I've checked everything...
It looks good.
You have ten seconds.
[Maka thinks]
Yes...
[Sid]
Five seconds left!
[Maka thinks]
It's all perfect.
Test is over!
Victory!
It's...over.
No...
[Patty] I got you now,
giraffe! Yes I do!
[Soul] It's been over since
I got strip searched.
[Student A]
Man... am I worn out.
[Student B] I know. That was
a tough one, huh?
[Student C] Yeah,
I think it was too hard.
[Student A]
I second that!
Come on. You gotta be
kidding me with this, Maka...
The test is all over...
And you're still studying?
No, no...
I made a mess while
I was studying earlier,
and when I was cleaning up,
I found this old photo album.
[Soul] Is that you with
your creepy dad?
He's so young!
[Maka] Uh-huh...
Papa was only eighteen
years old when I was born.
He used to read a lot
of books to me back then.
[Soul]
Huh...
You think your old man's
the reason you love to
read books so much now?
Maybe he is.
[cork popping]
[Blair and Death Scythe] Yea!
Congratulations, Papa...!
The results of the Super
Test-thingy have been posted.
That's something a
man can drink to!
I think it's great that
you spent three days
straight sending out
positive energy for Maka!
Maka sure is amazing huh...
...at the very top of her class,
just like my wife was.
You mean your ex-wife.
Yeah, my ex...
Listen, Blair...
can I ask you a favor?
Meow...
I wanted to get Maka
a present to congratulate
her on the test...
Could you casually find
out what her favorite book
is and buy it for her...?
Here, here's some money
for the book and a
letter from me to Maka.
Shouldn't you give
it to her yourself, Papa?
No, if I tried to give
it to her directly,
there's a good chance
she wouldn't accept it.
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
I can just tell that
you really love Maka.
If it's a book you want,
then consider it done.
Thank you Blair.
Oh, no...! I went and spent
the money on myself instead.
I couldn't resist
the temptation!
I'm used to being the one
who's doing the tempting...
Now I'm nothing
but a dirty cat burglar.
All I have to do is
shrink it a little,
and it'll be perfect...!
Pum-pum-pumpkin, pum pumpkin!
Now drop the
card inside, and done!
I'm home, Maka!
Hey... Welcome back.
There's pumpkin pie
if you're hungry.
[Blair]
Sounds good!
Here, Maka. I have a
present for you from your Papa.
It's to celebrate
your good test score.
What could it be?
Ta-da!
What could that
creep possibly be thinking,
sending sexy underwear
to his own daughter?!
Hold on, Maka... Um...
I think there's a card in here
that supposed to go with it.
Oh, great.
[Death Scythe]
Congratulations...!
I know you worked hard to
get such a high score.
That's why I'm sending
you this present.
I hope you can use it to
relax and have a little fun...
You've earned it...! From, Papa.
[Maka] What kind of
"fun" does he mean?
Just what kind of
girl does he think I am?
I'll bet Maka's enjoying
her present right now.
He's so... creepy!
I hate him.
Maka...
♪ closing song ♪
[Black Star]
The test is over!
[Maka]
No, it's not...
You still have to
take a make-up exam.
[Black Star] That
test is in the past...!
Truly big stars only
look into the future!
[Maka] Okay, well, the make-up
exam is in the future,
not the past.
[Black Star] What are
you trying to do,
trip me up with fancy language?
[Maka]
I'm not tripping you up;
I'm just tellin' it like it is.
[Black Star] Okay, fine. But
what am I supposed to do?
[Maka]
Try studying.
[Black Star]
Oh yeah that.
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Soul-eating Black Dragon...
Scaredy-cat Liz
and Her Merry Friends?
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!