There's no reason
to be surprised.
This was expected...
It's only natural that I am
the one still standing...
And they're the ones who
fell before me like insects ...
You're fools if you
expected something else.
Welcome to harsh
reality, children.
There are no surprises here.
Also...
...there is no fear.
A sound soul...
Dwells within a sound mind...
And a sound body.
Kishin Asura...
I hope you're ready...
Your soul is mine!
You're a persistent
one, aren't you...?
Returning to sanity after being
devoured by the black blood.
What's wrong?
You're trembling.
Are you afraid...?
Oh yes.
I think you're terrified.
Everything wrong in this
world is rooted in fear...
Frustration...
...failure...
...betrayal...
...anger...
...tragedy...
...and, of course...
Utter defeat.
Stop talking.
You don't have to hide it.
Poor girl.
Shut up!
Yelling won't get
you anywhere...
I'm not afraid of you.
But you are very
afraid of me, indeed...
Thanks to that,
I'll win this battle easily.
Say whatever you want...
It won't change anything.
She isn't shaking now...
She's ready to face him.
I am going to fight you.
And I'll win!
Let's do this!
Let's go!
Soul Resonance!
The Kishin hasn't
made a move yet.
Find your chance
and hit him hard!
You're so weak.
My final opponent,
and you're nothing more
than a pathetic little girl...
What a shame.
Maka...!
Get up now!
Your little friends were
so much stronger than you.
And look at how they ended up.
Move, Maka!
You're getting up...?
I think I prefer
you on the ground.
That position suits a
little weakling like you...
...but I can kill
you standing, too.
Can you make it?
Of course I can.
Let's go!
If this lasts too
long, I'll lose.
I have to find an opening
and strike as hard as I can...
Only one thing will work.
She's right.
We can only use one technique...
And that's...
Genie Hunter.
The Anti-Magic Wavelength...
An incredibly powerful
move handed down
to her from her mother.
The force that can erase evil...
...removing impurities
until only good remains.
Here she comes.
She's fighting the Kishin.
He's no ordinary opponent.
He won't be beaten so easily.
Damn it...
My daughter's down
there risking her life...
...and I can't do anything.
Maka...
Please...
...come back to me alive.
Now is our chance.
This is it, Maka.
Let's go!
Kishin Hunter!
A move that targets evil...
But let me ask you one thing...
Am I truly evil?
If you think I am, you're wrong.
The madness within
me that frightens
you so much isn't evil.
It's normal...
Everybody in this world has
a trace of insanity
resting within them...
Even you...
...madness makes no exceptions.
Screw you.
What a foul mouth...
I'll have to punish
you for that.
A sweet gesture...
...but how futile.
Soul...
Are you okay?
Soul!
They all sacrificed
themselves for you...
...but in the end,
is that truly a kindness?
They've only moved
the responsibility
onto your shoulders...
They've left you
the fear of failure.
Just shut the hell up.
But that isn't all, is it...?
There's the fear of death, too.
I thought I told you
to shut the hell up!
The fear of loneliness...
We can't forget that...
And also...
The fear of pain.
A primitive fear, all right,
but a cruel one nonetheless...
Besides...
It's effective enough
against someone like you.
A weak little human.
How can we be sure
it's still going on?
If something had happened
to the Kishin, we'd know...
The barrier he established
would start to fade.
For now we wait...
...and trust Maka to use her
technique to destroy the Kishin.
You're... wrong.
That's not what she needs.
Maka's strength...
Doesn't come from
some technique.
Yes...
You're right.
I am a weak human.
But this pain...
I've felt worse
than this before.
Much much worse than this.
This pain is nothing!
Let's see how much
pain you can handle then...
You can dodge this...
But if you do,
your friend will die.
That should finish it.
Back up on your feet again, huh?
Well, that won't last long.
What the--?
Impossible!
What magic is this?
What did you do?!
I see.
So that's what happened!
This girl is a weapon.
No, it's something else...
She's a meister all right,
but she also has weapon blood.
Why did the weapon within
her not awake until now?
There's no trace of
the fear she felt before.
Why not?
Oh, now I see.
She's remaining unconscious
so she won't feel fear.
She summons the
weapons without knowing it.
Now that I understand,
I can beat her.
This is a trick
I know how to fight.
Come here, girl!
Now I gotcha.
Go on and stab me.
I'm not afraid of pain...
Not at all.
But what about you?
Time to wake up.
Fighting while
your mind sleeps...
That's not fair.
There we go...
That's much better.
That suffocating
feeling you have now...
...that's fear.
You can let go now...
That's enough...
Let the madness carry you away,
and you'll be free from
all fear and pain.
Let go, and everything you
feel now will evaporate.
There's nothing more
you can do here.
Your friends have fallen.
Your big move failed.
There's no point
in continuing now...
Everything you've
done was for nothing.
You have no partner
to stand beside you...
Your body is
weak--bruised and beaten.
There's nothing you can
do now to defeat me...
You have nothing left.
I have nothing...
...left.
Yes, that's right...
You have nothing,
nothing at all.
It'll be all right then.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Is there something else
she can use besides the
Anti-Magic Wavelength...?
Some other technique?
Like I said...
Her greatest strength
isn't a technique...
It's something different.
Something in here.
Crona's right about that.
Look who's awake.
I'm back, baby!
And still as eloquent
as ever, I see.
What...?
What did you say?
Didn't you hear me?
I said it's going
to be all right.
What?
No it won't...!
Alright?!
The Genie Hunter isn't
what I need to defeat you.
How could she say that?
I went along with what
the teachers said...
I thought that move
was my only hope...
They were wrong...
That isn't my greatest power...
Not at all.
What are you saying?
You little fool.
Maka isn't the fool,
you jackass.
Do you all understand
what I'm talking about now?
Don't you get it yet...?
Maka may not be a
great star like I am...
...but she's got something
amazing, all right.
Maka's strength...
...isn't some special ability...
It's more.
It's something...
that can beat fear.
It's bravery!
That's all?
Bravery?
I don't understand you people.
You put faith in something as
fragile as one girl's bravery?
Stop it!
Don't look at me like that!
How can you be so
calm at a time like this?!
What's happening...?!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm academy
student Maka Albarn...
One star scythe meister.
Not what I meant...!
I'm not asking
you your name...!
You're standing
there so calmly...
That's not normal!
What are you?!
I'm just me...
Nothing more and nothing less.
She's making me nervous.
But I don't understand
why that is.
I'm so confused!
It's like the feeling you
get when you wake up
from a bad dream you
can't remember.
I've had enough of this.
You have to die now...
I'm going to kill
all of you...!
I don't have any other choice!
Shujaat...
What...?
What is that?
A postcard...
with a message.
But that doesn't matter...
It's none of your business.
None of my business?!
How can you talk
to me like that?!
You insolent--Oh no...
Whatever you're doing, stop!
No...
I won't.
I've come too far to stop now.
If I gave up, how could I
face the people who've
stood by me, supported
me for so long?
They're the reason I'm here.
They lent me their courage.
Now it's time to use my own.
It's time for me to
be brave for them.
That's ridiculous...
You don't know what
you're talking about!
Bravery is my armor...
and this is my weapon.
Fool!
You really think that pitiful
little fist will hurt me...?!
You'll accomplish nothing...!
Why can't you see how
useless it is to try...?
You should have given this
fight up a long time ago!
I don't understand
anything that's going on!
I don't get it.
Why do you have
so much faith in her?
She's weak...
She isn't special...
She's nothing more than a human.
What is bravery?
Kishin are you ready...?
I'm coming!
Go away!!
What's the point
in destroying me?
Madness won't disappear
just because I'm gone!
Another one will take my place!
There will be a new Kishin.
An heir to my madness...!
He will rain insanity upon
the world just as I have done!
That's the way this
world will always be!
Why can't you see
your struggle is pointless?!
I don't care!
Stay away!!
I will defeat you!
You didn't even scratch me...
Your fist wasn't
enough after all...
...you fool!
There's no way a
weak, talentless
little human like
you could beat me.
You didn't stand a chance!
What is this...?!
You just punched me.
Your fist isn't a weapon.
It's nothing special!
Exactly...
bravery's not special.
But that means...
everybody has it.
Everybody, huh?
Then it's just like madness.
The barrier's gone.
They did it?
Fool...!
Take a look.
Where's Maka?
Don't worry...
My Maka's too strong
to be defeated.
Finally...
It looks like it's over at last.
You did it, Maka.
You really are amazing...
Coolest partner ever.
The sky's all pretty now!
Well done.
We defeated the Kishin
and bad weather!
How bout that!
Ha! We win!
We win!
The sky's blue!
I surpassed god and
a cyoom-u-lo-nimbus!
Are you okay, Soul?
Well, we finally did it.
But there's still a lot
of work ahead of us.
Yeah, like rebuilding Death City
and repairing the academy.
Well... at least
we can celebrate
that the Kishin's
gone now, right?
We can't be too happy.
People still
inhabit this world...
...there will always be
more evil to face.
We were able to scrape through
this time because of Maka...
But sooner or later
another Kishin will rise up.
It'll be okay.
When it does come,
we'll be there...
Besides...
...there's a lot
more to people than
evil thoughts and bad deeds.
There's bravery.
Everybody has that...
Right in here.
♪ closing song ♪