A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
It's all right, Ashura.
I'll be by your side, watching
over you and protecting you.
Like this...
Always and forever.
♪ opening song  ♪
What's happening?
Everything is so confusing.
Guilty!
You betrayed us!
There's too much going
on at one time...
I can't make sense of it all.
And right now...
...it's difficult to tell
what the academy's
real objective is in all this.
The Kishin's free...
...and the world is about to
be consumed by madness.
That's where our
focus should be.
After all, the academy
was founded
in the first place to
fight the Kishin.
That I understand...
...but what about everything
else they've done...?
What happens now?
Trouble sleeping?
Leave me alone.
Acting like this isn't gonna
help you out any tomorrow...
The mission's gonna
be difficult enough as it is.
Hey, Soul.
Are they doing the right thing?
Who?
What're you talking about?
The academy...
I don't understand what
they're doing anymore...
They've completely stopped
looking for Professor Stein.
Then there's all that
other stuff Kid told us about...
And also...
What about poor Crona...?
He's still locked
up in that cell.
No idea...
You know as much as I do.
Sitting in the dark and
pouting isn't gonna help...
Just get some sleep.
Be careful out
there today, you two.
Hah...! We can handle
this, no problem...
We'll destroy the Kishin and
be back before you even know it.
Something wrong?
Don't worry about her.
She'll snap out of it soon.
Let's do this.
Everyone's working so hard
to stop this Kishin guy...
I want to help defeat him too!
Meow!
Charge Baba Yaga's Castle!
o~ Things are Kind of Gloomy?
The objective
of today's mission...
Destroy the Kishin Ashura.
In addition, we will target
those who have sided with
the Kishin including
the witch Arachnay,
and the members of her
organization Arachnophobia.
We will be launching an
attack on their base...
Lies.
Cover-ups...
Repeated without hesitation.
While they turn a blind eye
to everything else
but their mission.
The madness is spreading.
It must be stopped...
before it's too late.
Which means we will also
be battling against time.
Our first objective...
Destroy the Kishin.
Second...
We obliterate the
madness machine.
And then...
the madness relay stations.
And finally...
Arachnay...
Kill her...
...and destroy her organization.
Fine then...
They can ignore
it all if they want...
But they can't make me forget.
We have every
confidence in your skills.
But we realize the
risk of coming
into contact with the Kishin...
So do not forget to
take your doses of
madness suppressant
before you leave.
And now...
...a word from Lord Death.
Students!
Do your best, okay...?
Victory!
That's it?
All right...
The operation will now commence.
First destination...
Baba Yaga Castle.
Excuse me, Mr. Sid.
There's something
I wanted to ask you.
Go ahead.
It's about Crona.
What're they going
to do with him...?
Please tell me...
I know you know.
Crona's been exiled, Maka.
He was a spy...
...and a traitor...
He's done a lot of
damage to the academy...
Given that...
...exile is lenient.
Exile...?
But where can he go?
When I was alive,
I had tight lips...
I knew how to keep a secret...
That's the kind of man I was...
But I did talk out
loud to myself at times.
Maybe Crona's exile
is just a cover...
Maybe he left with Miss Marie...
...to go after Medusa.
With Miss Marie...
...but why?
Yesterday...
Marie resigned...
She's no longer
with the academy.
Crona is going to settle things
with Medusa once and for all.
Medusa.
It's all right...
Miss Marie will be
there to back him up...
You should focus
on today's operation.
We're counting on you and
your Anti-Magic Wavelength...
Don't let us down.
So that's it.
That's how they're
gonna handle it...?
This is the adults'
great solution?
Maka...
I'm sorry.
What is it, Crona...?
What's wrong?
Oh, uh...
it's nothing.
Fine...
...then let's keep moving.
I was in this same
desert not long ago.
I thought I was escaping.
This time...
...this time it's different.
Maka...
I'm sorry I had to lie.
But...
I'm not running anymore.
We should split our
forces into thirds
and make our attack
on three fronts.
And the soldiers in charge of
demolishing the relay stations
need to synchronize
their attacks
so they all happen at one time.
This is the first attack
on so grand a scale
since the academy was founded.
That suppressant...
...do you really think it'll be
effective against the madness?
If such a medicine
actually existed,
I would have delivered it
throughout the world already.
I thought so.
Suppressing panic...
...an obvious tactic.
Lord Death...
What I'd like to know is
why I'm stationed here.
Yeah, that is a good question.
You were the one
who made that call!
Given what we're up against,
I don't think we can have too
many forces in the field...
Based on my analysis, it
wouldn't hurt to have
all the Death Scythes
fighting out there.
Easier said than done, Azusa.
Yikes!
We're battling a Kishin today...
...yet for some reason
you're keeping me here,
and you sent Marie and
Kid off on assignments
that have nothing to do
with the fighting...
If you ask me,
it defies common sense.
We can't know for
sure what's going
to happen on the
battlefield today...
Surely you'll agree the
best plan of action
is to prepare for
all possibilities.
There you see now...!
Not so simple!
Oh dear!
Whatever they say...
I still think our forces
are too spread out.
Why don't you put
that scary face away
and come have a cup of tea?
Pull up a seat!
There's some yummy
cake over here!
All right, you two!.
Shape up!
I don't know how
to handle this woman.
What was that?
Nothing!
Well...
I'm sure things will
sort themselves out...
in the meantime,
we'll focus on dealing
with each new
problem as it arises.
Wonderful.
I told Lord Death I wouldn't
pause to accept some help.
Hi, Mister Joe.
I'm Blair the cat...!
Starting today,
I'm your new assistant.
Exciting, huh?
I'm Lisa from Chupacabra!
And my name's Arisa.
But I don't think he
understood my request!
Ha.
Meow, meow!
We are now entering
Arachnophobia's territory.
All forces...
Make sure you're in place.
Ready yourselves for the attack.
Is there something
bothering you, Maka?
No.
It's nothing.
Uh-oh.
You're not getting
cold feet, are you...?
Because there's nothing
to be afraid of...!..
Not as long
as I'm here, anyway...!
With a big star like me around,
this is the safest place
in the entire world!
If you don't quiet down,
they'll know we're here.
Are you still thinking about
that crap from last night?
Maybe.
You have to keep your
head in the game today...
...otherwise, the whole
thing will fall apart.
You of all people
should know that!
Don't worry, Soul.
I'm sure Maka's going
to do really well today...
Sid and Lord Death both said
her Anti-Magic Wavelength
might be all we need.
They're counting on
a technique I can't master...
It's ridiculous.
But there's more
to it than that.
The Genie Hunter's
not the only thing
that makes you a great fighter.
There's nothing
that's great about me.
Damn...! Quit being
such a perfectionist!
Yeah, like that'll happen!
Black Star, will you
please be quiet?!
Just leave me alone, guys.
You had a conversation with
Sid before we left, didn't you?
What, you mean about
the Genie Hunter move...?
I told you, it's ridiculous.
No, not that...
About Miss Marie and Crona.
Do you understand
what's really going on...?
Why it had to
be the two of them?
The DWMA made
a deal with Medusa...
...because of that,
we can't harm her.
Lord Death gave his word not to.
But Crona's
an exile, isn't he...?
And Miss Marie
quit her teaching job.
Lord Death's making some
pretty low moves these days...
There might be something
in what Kid told us...
So maybe we really can't
trust the academy anymore.
Soul's right...
That's a sneaky plan.
I was wondering why
Kid's not here with us...
Maybe this has
something to do with it.
We can't afford to
freak out about
every little thing that
comes our way right now.
If you ask me,
it's the other way around.
We can't afford not to.
Don't know about you,
but I'm here to win...
I'm gonna take down
every last one of 'em.
And when that's over...
I'll surpass God.
Great.
Here he goes again.
What should I do?
You can sleep soundly, Asura.
It's okay...
As long as I'm
here by your side.
You'll see my dear one...
Before much longer, the world
will be utterly consumed
by delicious madness.
Until then, you'll stay here
with me where you'll be safe.
Lady Arachne...
...we have an issue.
Let's hear it.
We have detected DWMA forces.
Oh really?
Yes, my lady.
And it appears they're searching
for a way into Baba Yaga Castle.
So it would seem...
They shouldn't have been able
to find the castle's
location, though.
I don't think
storming the castle
is their only
objective, either.
They seem to have
deployed six additional
squads to other areas.
Six forces?
They're targeting
the relay stations.
The bulk of their forces will
be arriving at our gates soon.
How do they know?
Medusa...!
It must have been.
Prepare for a counterattack...
I want all of the
troops out there...
The DWMA must be stopped,
no matter what.
Right.
Hurry...!
Move, you maggots!
We've got a
battle to fight here!
I want everyone prepared.
Understood?
Yes!
It's finally time.
I'm gonna grind
these fools into dust!
Look at this, Stein...
It's beginning.
We don't want to
miss one minute of this.
A new world order
is going to be born today.
Everything is about to change.
This is the Fifth...
We're in place.
Third Squadron here...
We are in position.
The Seventh is ready to go.
Captain...
We're ready...
All squads in place.
All right...
Listen up, everyon--
Let's go!
Rip 'em apart!
Triple Speed Saw Leg!
All clear...!
Now move it!
That was a familiar attack...
Looks like an
old friend of mine.
Saw man...
...we meet again, do we?
This is gonna be the
last time for you, punk!
The enemy...!
Commence battle at once men!
Yeah...! I hope these
guys are ready
to see one hell of
a performance.
Not yet, Black Star.
Hold on.
What do you think Maka?
The Kishin has to be defeated...
The academy is
doing the right thing.
But still...
Even knowing that...
There's no way I can abandon
Professor Stein and Crona...
That's not who I am.
We have to be careful about
who at the academy we trust.
I can't just
forget about them...
...but I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
What do I do?!
Ugh!
Would you stop
being such a crybaby...?!
Wah, wah, wah!
Whine, whine, whine!
What the hell's wrong with you?
What is your problem...?
Why are you talking
to me like that?
Because you have
to make a decision.
Get a grip, Maka...!
Decide what you're going to do!
Yes...
I see now.
You know, it's funny...
My dad always used to warn me
to choose my friends wisely...
...and he was right.
Look at me...
...a perfect student...
Thanks to you...
I'm a rule breaker.
Right!
That's it...
Sorry, Black Star...
...the rest is up to you!
What's with her?
From now on, I'm gonna
be doing things my way!
It's all you, man.
Hey!
Who's she kidding...?
Maka couldn't be more wrong.
I don't care what she says,
she's still a perfect student.
Hang on, Crona!
I'm coming!
♪ closing song ♪
I've made up my mind.
Now I just have to
run toward my goal!
Exactly...!
Sometimes in life
you need to run ahead...
But then again, sometimes
you need to stand still.
Uh, Miss Marie...?
To run or to stand
still--that is the question.
Huh?
Hmm, let's see here...
Maybe I could try
both at the same time!
That won't work!
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Last Magic Tool...
Mission Impossible
for Unarmed Kid?
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!