A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
What's going to happen next?
At this point, who knows?
But...
...we can be sure about
one thing at least...
With the Kishin around...
...the whole world'll
be buried in madness.
Did Medusa really
believe she'd be
able to beat such an opponent?
Which do you mean?
The Kishin or the Grim Reaper?
Whichever...
It seems impossible either way.
I wish I knew what
was going on in there.
Black Star,
are you ready for this?
Huh?
We've gotta find a
way to hold him back.
Hah...! Hold him back?
Gimme a break...
I don't know about you but
I got bigger plans than that.
I'm gonna kill this guy!
Maka.
Is it you?
Yeah...
Who were you expecting?
It's Soul.
♪ opening song ♪
It is you!
I'm so relieved!
This isn't over, though...
I'm locked in this room...
I relied too much
on the black blood...
...and because of that,
most of my soul
has been consumed
by its insanity.
Yeah... I know...
...that's why I'm
here to get you.
Hurry up... We need to
get out of this room!
We can't.
The door's gone.
It disappeared behind you
as soon as you walked in.
Is there another way?
If I knew that, do you think
I'd still be hanging around?
Yeah, okay, you've
got a good point.
Window?
None at all.
We could break through the wall.
Nope.
Or rip up the floor
and dig a tunnel?
No way.
Then we'll never get outta here.
Actually, there is a way...
Really?
The one and only
way out of here.
Sink or Swim...
The Men Who Transcend the Gods?
Death Cannon.
Thanks for the
excellent massage.
It was quite rejuvenating.
I thought I was never going to
get that crick out of my neck.
We need to do something...
We're losing ground quickly.
"Losing ground?"...
But that implies you'd
gained some to begin with.
When you're up against a power
as strong as mine is, it's not a
question of gaining ground
or making progress.
It's a question
of staying alive.
Unfortunately for you,
that particular question isn't
going to have a pleasant answer.
You're right...
...with the level of
attack we're using now...
...we're hard pressed
to even put a dent in you.
In which case...
Huh?
We're just going to have
to attack you even
harder, aren't we?
Dad...
I'm sorry...
I didn't understand
what you were doing...
I doubted you and
every move you made...
Then the Kishin defeated you...
And it's all my fault.
Pathetic...
Useless...!
I don't deserve to be his son.
I wish...
I wish I'd trusted him...
Things would be different now...
I failed my father...
Maybe I don't have
what it takes to do this.
But...
I can try...
Hear me now, Asura!
Die, in the name
of the Grim Reaper!
Liz, Patty...
Ready?
--Yes!
--Yeah!
Let's go Soul Resonance!
His soul is so strong!
Black Star...
Follow my lead now...
I'll need some back up.
That's a low move, Kid.
No way!
Stealing my spotlight
at a time like this?!
We don't have
time to fool around.
Can't you see that right now,
all that matters is
destroying him?!
I need you to hold him
back until I'm ready.
What'll you do?
This next shot...
I'm giving it all I have...
There will be no second chances.
Back me up.
Hell no!
What?!
That plan doesn't work for me...
First, I'll charge
right at 'im...
Then you can join the fight and
back me up when you're ready.
Uh, Black Star...
I'm the star of this
show 'till it's over.
Have it your way.
K...
Kid!!!
A way out?
Great, so what should we do?
Is that it...?
A box?
Looks like it's locked.
What the--?
Careful...
Go easy on that, okay?
You gotta be gentle.
It's my courage that's
locked up in there.
Liar!
It isn't my
courage in here...!..
Do you hear me, Maka?
It's me locked inside...!
Don't you get it?
Maka...! Look...
I'm down here...!
I'm inside the box!
This is all because
of the black blood...
I used it too much,
and now my courage's
trapped inside that box.
That's why we need to open it...
So we can both
get out of this room.
He's lying, Maka...! It's me!
I sealed myself in here...
...before the black
blood could take over.
If you open the box,
my soul will be consumed
by the black blood!
I tried everything I
could possibly think of,
but nothing I did
would open it.
He only wants you to open
it for him so he can
get in here and devour
what's left of me.
Please see that...!
It isn't me out there...!
It's the demon...
Please, Maka!
Makaaaa!!
The thing is...
I'm pretty sure you're the
only one who can get it open.
Yeah...?
I open this...
...and then you'll be
able to get out?
Yeah, exactly...
Just look.
The key's in your hand.
You idiot...!
Don't listen to him...!
Do not open it!
You know that isn't me, Maka!
Kid...
Damn you!
Uh uh uh...
You blame me for this?
That's not fair.
I don't recall inviting you to
follow me in here.
That choice was yours.
Kid what the heck's
going on here...?
I've never seen your soul
do something like that before!
I have no idea what's happening,
but it sure is cool, huh, sis?
Whatever it is...
...we'd better think of
something to do now!
Yea!
Huh?
What's that?
The Lines of Sanzu.
I remember you now...
You're the Grim Reaper's little
son, aren't you...? Excellent.
I can deal with you the same
way I dealt with your father.
You've got the
wrong target, dude!
You shouldn't underestimate me.
I'm the one who's gonna
destroy you, not him...!
Take your eyes off
me for a second,
and it'll be the
last thing you do!
Shut up, insect!
Didn't I tell you?
Don't take your eyes off me!
Black Star Big Waaaave!
Damn!
Where're you lookin'...?
I'm here!
Nope...!
Over here! Here!
Right here, ya slowpoke!
Stop it right now!
The real one is...
Right here!
I got you that time!
Yahoo!
What?!
I warned you, didn't I?
I'm the one who's
gonna destroy you!
Now, Kid!
Fire away.
Hey look at the
stripes in his hair!
They're all connect-y!
Resonance rate is at
two thousand percent?!
Impossible!
And the noise level...!
It's at zero!
Feedback complete...
We're ready to fire!
Let's go!
Woo-hoo...!
We did it...!
We got the Kishin, Patty!
Kid!
What's wrong?!
That was one hell of a shot.
But what happened to Kid?
It's no big deal.
This is Kid we're talking about.
It'll take more
than that to kill him.
Black Star?
Oh no!
Come on...
Don't get so upset, Tsubaki...
If he's back, that can
only mean one thing.
I knew it...
Today's the day
I'm gonna fulfill
my destiny and surpass god!
Any movement down there?
Something must've happened...
There's a crack in the
Grim Reaper's mask
that wasn't there before.
Are you all right, Death Scythe?
Yeah...
could be a lot worse.
Can't you use your Clairvoyance
to see what's going on with the
students and the Kishin
inside the barrier?
I can't...
...not without a pre-established
link to at least one of them.
Then for all we know, the
battle could already be over.
Maybe they beat him.
Fool!
Nothing has been decided yet...
The battle's still going on.
What...?
Are you sure about that?
Fool...!
Of course I am!
Does that mean you can
see what's going on insi--
Fool...!
Silence.
I require a cup of tea
before I deign to answer that.
Um how about coffee instead?
Fool...! I said tea...
And I mean tea!
This guy...!
Hey everybody...
What's all the commotion?
Stein!
When did you get back here?!
Why did you miss me...?
I guess I should apologize
for causing so much trouble.
A little late for that.
This is serious...
Maka, Black Star, and Kid
are all inside that barrier,
fighting the Kishin
as we speak.
Maka...
Then it's up to her...
to Maka...
We were right about it coming
down to Genie Hunter.
Her mother's technique.
Maka's Genie Hunter.
Well...
...open it...
...go on...
...do it now...
Hurry up.
Don't do it...!
Don't open the box!
What are you doing?
Open it and we can go.
Sure... but first...
...tell me something...
Pathetic!
If you're not gonna
open it, I will.
I'm not giving you the key.
What?!
Now...
...tell me who you are.
Maka...
What're you talking about...?
You know me.
You're not Soul.
Shut up...!
Of course I am.
Just look at me!
Liar.
Soul would never ask me
for something like this.
I'm asking because
there's no other way!
Okay...
...tell me why you
closed the door!
The real Soul never
would have closed it...
Not if it would trap me too...
He would have told
me to turn back.
I know my partner.
And you're not him.
Yes...!
Nice once, Maka.
You're not an idiot.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, half right at least.
I'm not the Soul you knew.
It's you.
Yes...
I may not look like your good
friend Soul, but I assure you,
I'm a genuine soul eater.
And I am a part
of Soul as well...
...just as he, too,
is a part of me...
Soul and I work together
combined in a single body.
We're partners, he and I,
the kind that can't be
separated, no matter what.
That's why I say
you're only half right.
I am Soul, but at
the same time, I'm not.
It's complicated, I know.
I hope I'm not confusing you.
So the real Soul
is inside this box.
Yes...
That's correct...
Funny, isn't it?
Who would think such a small box
could hold all his arrogance...?
But, no matter...
I don't need him anymore...
My plan is very nearly complete.
The world is nearly mine now.
I can almost taste my success.
You're the only thing
standing in my way...
But not for too much longer.
You are going to do what I say.
Do it...
...refusing to open the
box won't help anything...
If you don't unlock
it, you'll have the
pleasure of watching
while Soul and I die.
So, you have two choices...
Keep the box closed and kill me,
along with your dear friend...
...or open it and
meet a new Soul...
...one who's been
consumed by the
madness of the black blood...
Which will it be?
Soul is actually in here,
though, right?
He absolutely is.
Right.
Then I'll open it...
I have to.
You what?!
Are you the crazy one?!
Haven't you heard
a thing he's said?!
That's the right decision.
I knew you weren't
the type of girl
who would abandon her partner.
Now...
...go ahead...
...go on and open it.
Yes... I will...
...but I won't let the
insanity take Soul.
I'll save him.
I swear it!
I'm coming, Soul!
I'm here!
Maka!
What...
what happened?
Impossible!
You are the biggest
moron, Maka...
Such an idiot...
But then of course that's
what makes you the
coolest partner a
weapon could have.
Damn...
...after everything I've done,
I'm stuck back here again?
What are you getting so
worked up about, little guy?
Little guy?
Pathetic.
You're getting rid
of me, aren't you?
How could I do
something like that?
You're still a part
of me, after all...
...and so...
I'll have to accept you.
We made it back.
Yeah...
thanks to you, we did.
Where did Kid and
Black Star go?
Kid!
Black Star!
There's no reason
to be surprised.
As expected...
I am the one still standing.
And they are the ones
who fell before me...
...like insects.
You're fools if you expected
some other outcome than this.
Welcome to
harsh reality, children.
There are no surprises here...
...and no uncertainty.
Also...
There is no fear.
♪ closing song ♪
On the final episode
of Soul Eater...
The Word is Bravery!
Watch it...
Or I'll take your soul!