[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Hero sighs]
So... so this is...
The Holy Sword Excalibur?
Victory and glory?!
I could become a famous hero?
With this legendary sword
as a partner, even someone
like me could
achieve everlasting
renown and magnificence!
It's decided!
I'm going after the
Holy Sword, Excalibur!
[All]
Shh!!
[Hero]
Sorry... sorry.
♪ opening song ♪
[Green Hat Boy]
Hey, Hero.
What's up?
[Green Hat Boy]
Yeah, man, so, listen...
...could you go buy
us some sandwiches?
What...? Why're you asking me?
[Green Hat Boy]
Please, dude...
This is something
only you can do.
We're countin'
on you man. Seriously.
It's something that
only I can do...?
Leave it to me!
[Kim]
Hey! Don't forget about us!
[Jacqueline]
Yeah, we're parched...
We could really
use a couple sodas.
It's something else
only you can do, Hero...
Thank you!
[Black Star]
Yo, Hero...!
C'mere a sec.
Okay, what is it, Black Star?
[Black Star] The usual.
I need you for practice.
Ow ow ow!
I'm gonna die!
Do you think this
move hurts enough?
Is it difficult to get out of?
[HERO] ...Eyeballs are gonna
pop out of my head! Ow! Ow! Ow!
He could still use
some more practice.
Hero's kind of
misnamed, isn't he?
He's a regular student
like the rest of us...
He's just...
...an ordinary guy.
You could use a lesson or
two on how to be cool, man.
Damn... Reaching
the Holy Sword's
the only chance I've got.
It's time to say farewell to
the academy's
favorite errand boy!
I shall be... transformed!
[Maka] The Legend
of the Holy Sword 3:
The Academy Gang Leader's Tale?
I am the great Black Star!
No one can stop me...
...'cause I'm
the invincible man!
I'm lookin' so cool
while walkin' to school...!
Right, Tsubaki!
Yeah!
Uh...Hey...What the...? Eh?
Isn't it early for fighting?
[Hero laughs]
Please...!
What a pitiful bunch you are.
I've been reborn as a true hero.
Ordinary people like you don't
stand a chance against me.
You mean that
Hero kid did this?
[Excalibur] This academy
is nothing special.
Uhh... Him again?!
[Excalibur] My legend is far
more impressive than anything
that has happened
at this school.
[Excalibur] All students and
meisters must hear it!
[Excalibur]
Fool!
My legend dates back to
the twelfth century, you see...
It began on a midsummer day
with the sun blazing overhead...
No, wait...
...it was a blustery autumn day.
I was an unsavory fellow
back when it all started...
...which was in
the winter, as I recall...
I ran with a tough crowd.
All the hot babes fought
over me that summer...
Yes, yes that's right.
It was summer...
...a scorching midsummer day!
I was a dangerous
man at the time...
...and yet refined somehow...
Everyone thought so.
They still think so,
to this day...
Although maybe they didn't
think so as much back then...
...but they definitely
said I was dangerous,
I'm sure of it...
...and I know I've
always been refined...
...so they must have
been thinking it...
Yes, yes indeed.
Everyone thought and said
and talked about
how amazing I was...
I'm still amazing, of course,
but no longer the bad boy
that I was back then...
...on that chill,
frozen winter day.
I will continue the
retelling of my legend.
[All]
Lame...
[Excalibur]
But first...
There will be
a five minute break...
Stand still and await my return.
[Black Star]
Hold on, you freak!
[Excalibur]
What do you want...?
The stated five minute
break hasn't passed yet.
Say, don't I know you?
Yeah... It was a
really memorable--
You can't wait
five minutes...? Fool!
Watch the stick, dude.
Did you see before,
Black Star...
...my incredible strength?
I'm no longer the
miserable loser I was...
The Holy Sword has
changed all that.
I have been transformed
into a powerful hero.
Getting your hands on a
particular weapon doesn't
necessarily change you at all.
Besides, what could
possibly be worth having to
put up with
this cane-waving freak?
Oh, please...
The one thousand provisions
I must observe to be Excalibur's
meister are so easy to handle
I could do it in my sleep.
It seems to me
the real question is...
How come you weren't
able to handle the Holy Sword?
You're a real idiot...
Damn... Have you even gotten
to the part about the five
hour storytelling parties yet?
[Excalibur]
Now that you mention it,
my legend began on
the same day as today...
...a Tuesday or a Wednesday.
Or a Saturday, perhaps...
Either make up your
mind or shut up.
[Excalibur]
No, it was on Monday...
...though I suppose it
could have been a
Tuesday or Wednesday...
Thursday is a
distinct possibility...
...or Friday even...
Although Monday
does sound right...
...and Saturday is a
lovely day to begin a legend...
...perhaps it was Thursday...
...or Tuesday...
...maybe Wednesday or Friday...?
There's always Monday, too...
...and Saturday,
we can't forget Saturday...
No, no, it was
almost certainly on a...
[Black Star raving]
Shut up or I'll kill you!!
I can't take it anymore!
[Excalibur]
We fight, then?
[Hero]
A fight, huh?
I'd like a piece of that action.
--♪ Su su su su
sushi roll roll. ♪
I'd like to check out what
this legendary sword can do.
[Kid] Same here.
With that guy around...
It's impossible
to maintain one's sanity.
Look at the stupid alien!
Wanna fight?
[Crowd murmurs]
[Hero]
Kilik Rung...
Black Star...
Death the Kid...
A battle between the
three best fighters in
the academy and Excalibur...
A worthy match-up.
I'll be joining the
fight as well, so you can
see my new abilities
up close and personal.
Excalibur!
[crowd murmurs]
Victory... and glory...
...are mine now!
He is somewhat intimidating.
When all is said and done,
the three of you will be
nothing more than a
footnote in the legend
of the Holy Sword Excalibur.
Shut uuuuuup!
Don't you remember
who you are?!
Hero wouldn't dare
talk like that!
My new name...
...is Hero the Brave.
I am Hero the Brave!
Oh yeah?!
Well, take this...!
Heaven's Strike,
Conan the Great!
[Hero] If you do
not follow the light...
...no blow you strike will
ever touch Hero the Brave.
[Kilik]
Now I'm getting fired up!
Pot of Fire... Triple F!
Liz. Patty...
Fire Styx Shot.
What?!
[Kid]
Where is he?
[Hero] With this...
you will be defeated.
Last move...
Hero the Atomic.
[huge blast]
[Unknown boy 1]
Awesome...
All he had to do was
name the technique,
and they were deep fried.
[Unknown boy 2]
I don't even know what he did.
So guys...
What do you think
about the new me?
Pretty powerful, aren't I?
[Death] And thus, the DWMA
was taken over by Hero,
former failed meister
and total loser.
What will become
of the academy now...?
You'll have to wait until
after the break to find out!
[girls screaming]
This is the perfect example
of my soon to be
legendary powers...
I've made it into
the girls' locker room.
[All]
Go away!!
[Kim and Jacqueline screaming]
What now?
Aw...! If you don't like it,
you'll have to find
a way to defeat me!
You dirty pervert!
Excalibur's not
in his usual spot.
[Fairies]
Finally! We're free!
I can't believe he's gone!
[students murmur]
Everybody worships me
now that I'm Hero the Brave.
The ecstasy and
uncertainty of being
the chosen one is overwhelming.
He talks an awful lot about
being transformed
and that sort of thing...
But all that's really changed
is now he's a jackass.
[Maka]
It's Ox!
How could he do such an
awful thing to my beloved Kim?!
Hero, you're a dead man!
--[Soul] Ox!
--[Maka] Hold on a sec!
Calm down and
take a breath, Ox.
Look at those two.
I wonder how much longer
they'll be able to
pull this off.
[Ox]
We have to remember,
this is Hero.
He's a perpetual failure.
He'll get tired of the thousand
provisions and give up
before too much longer.
You're getting scary, Ox.
[Excalibur] The 1000 Provisions
of The Holy Sword Excalibur...
Number 22:
On a refreshing morning,
start out with a
refreshing greeting.
[rooster crows]
[Excalibur]
Hero...! Good morning!
And a very good
morning to you, Excalibur.
Now, let us begin another
great day shall we?
This day will never come again,
so we should spend
it together. Let's enjoy!
[Excalibur and Hero laugh]
I'll kill 'em!
[Excalibur] Number Four
Hundred and Fifty-Two...
Attendance at the five-hour
storytelling party is
absolutely mandatory.
[Excalibur]
Your twenties will be the
great transitional
period of your life...
It is a time of crossroads,
of immense change,
of incredible uncertainty...
Indeed, my twenties were
such a period for me...
That was when I evolved
from a no-good trouble maker
to the legendary sword
you see before you today...
Many men envied my hairstyle,
you see, and they were
inspired to copy it...
...and formed a fringe group...
...a sort of cult,
if you will...
...dedicated to the adoration
of my daring hairstyle...
They met every week...
...or was it every day...
...to discuss...
As you may have noticed,
humans are very young
from the time they are
born until some years later...
I, however, was born
old and wise,
and I would often discuss
abstract philosophical...
[Excalibur]
That is all!
[Hero clapping alone]
[Excalibur] Number Five
Hundred and Seventy-Eight:
The hero must never tell a lie.
[Holmes] So, what
you're telling me
is that you didn't
see anything?
That's correct I swear,
sir, I didn't see anything.
[Holmes] I see... But perhaps
you know something about someone
who did see something.
[Movie Lady] No, I don't know
anything about anybody
who saw anything anywhere.
[Holmes]
Is that so?
This is a complicated
case indeed...
You see, no one saw
you see nothing...
...so how can we confirm
that you don't know
anything or anyone anywhere?
[Watson]
Holmes...
...have you discovered anything?
[Holmes] Yes, I believe
I have a viable theory.
Indeed? What do you think?
[Excalibur]
This man is the culprit!
That's right...!
This man is the brother
of the girl who went missing
ten years ago and the author
of this terribly tragic tale
of revenge and murder.
Wow...! You figured it all out!
[All]
Sit down!
[Hero]
Hey...!
Please don't
throw things...! Ow!
[Excalibur]
Number Two Hundred and Two:
Only the grandest
of toilets is acceptable.
It's grand, all right...
But did he have to put it here?
[Hero] This was the only
location with enough room.
[Excalibur] Number Six
Hundred and Sixty-Seven...
You will praise
Excalibur at all times.
Magnificent Excalibur!
Munificent Excalibur!
Magnanimous Excalibur!
[Excalibur] Number One Hundred
and Seventy-Two: Seek harmony.
Seek it thus...
First, a haircut.
No, stop! Hold it!
[Excalibur]
Number Seventy-Five:
Celebrate Excalibur's
birthday in grand style.
[Hero]
When is your birthday?
[Excalibur]
Every day!
[All]
Lame!
Really...?!
Then I'll think of
three hundred and sixty
five ways to celebrate,
and each one will be
better than the one before.
[All]
No way!
[Excalibur]
Number Six Hundred and Two:
Meals will be prepared with
the freshest ingredients.
For today's special ingredient
we will be using the
always-delectable red king crab.
[TV Lady] Ooh! It looks
simply delicious!
[Excalibur]
I want some red king crab.
Yes! Right away!
[Excalibur]
Seconds.
Gladly, sir!
[All]
Why?!
[Excalibur]
Well done!
You have met the
one thousand provisions!
[Hero]
Thank you so much!
[Excalibur] As a reward,
I'll sing you a song...
Listen carefully.
[Hero]
Yea!
[Excalibur]
♪ Excalibur! ♪
♪ From the United K... ♪
♪ I'm looking for heaven... ♪
♪ I'm going to California! ♪
♪ Excalibur! ♪
♪ Excalibur, Excalibur, ♪
♪ Excalibur, Excalibur,
Excalibur... ♪
[Fairies celebrating]
This is sooo nice not
having him around!
Excuse me, Lord Death...
What we discussed earlier?
Yes sir. It's about the
legendary Holy Sword
Excalibur, sir.
[Excalibur] The legendary
Holy Sword Excalibur.
By wielding it, Hero has
become sort of a gang
leader within the DWMA.
[Death] Being a gang leader
means wearing steel-toed boots,
dressing horribly,
and picking fights.
And also keeping
one's followers happy...
...a job often easier
said than done...
Their current project is
setting up a cheer squad.
[Death]
Hold on a second...
...since when does the
DWMA have a student gang?
I know, it's news to me too.
[Death]
And here I thought we
were done with
that sort of thing.
Students will always look
for someone to lead them.
[Excalibur]
♪ Excalibur, Excalibur, ♪
♪ Excalibur, Excalibur. ♪
[Student 4]
You're amazing, Hero!
[Student 5] Performing all of
those thousand tasks!
[Student 6] You have an
incredible partner!
[Hero] I am truly a
man to be revered!
Everyone, look...!
Behold my splendor...!
Worship me!
Does he seem a little
overconfident to you, Soul?
Well... in a way,
I guess he has
found his ideal partner.
No, say it isn't so!
How could this
happen to Hero,
of all people!
It can't be true!
[Death] Stories begin
and stories end...
Often we cannot predict the
outcome of a particular tale.
For example,
everyone thought the
unique bond between
Hero and the Holy Sword
would last forever...
They were wrong.
[Hero] Today was
a perfect day, huh?
[Excalibur] Have you
forgotten provision number
five hundred and seventy three?
Always walk three
steps behind me.
Of course, I'm sorry.
[Excalibur]
Now... on our way.
[Excalibur sneezes]
[Excalibur]
Only a sneezing fit...
Let's go.
[Excalibur sneezes non-stop]
[Hero]
Sneezing?
[Fairies partying]
[Black Star]
Yo, Hero!
[Hero] Ah, Good morning,
Black Star...
Would you like a sandwich...
...or a soda, maybe?
Huh...? That's odd...
It seems like you're back
to your normal self again....
What happened to Excalibur?
Oh, yeah, that...
I put it back again...
stupid sword.
I don't get it...?
You guys were getting
along so well, weren't you?
[Hero]
The sneezes...
Once he started
those sneezing fits,
there was no way to stop it.
Sneezing's gross...
Spit and snot go flying...
...it goes everywhere.
I can't stand it.
Seriously, the damn thing
would be better off dead.
That's what finally got to you?
Being transformed was nice
while it lasted, I guess...
Hey... do you know
any other way to
completely change a person?
Yeah...
...there's obviously
a better way.
Try to be like me!
I'm the man
who'll surpass God!
Just watching me and doing
like I do will transform
you in no time!
Once you go 'Black Star,'
you'll never go back.
Real helpful...
Maybe I'll just start with
some weight training for now.
[Excalibur] Welcome to
the storytelling party...!
We will begin with
my personal history.
I shall recount my legend
from its historic beginning!
[Excalibur sneezes]
By the way, this top hat of mine
is lined with the finest quality
English seaweed roll.
[All]
Lame!!
♪ closing song ♪
[Black Star] Ya-hoo!
It's finally over...!
I'll never have to see
that obnoxious moron again!
[Excalibur] Fool! You shouldn't
make that assumption!
[Black Star]
What the--
I thought you left...?!
Take a hint, dude...
Go be lame somewhere
else, would ya?!
[Excalibur] Fool! You may not be
able to understand the
subtle genius of my character,
but I assure you
there are others who do.
[Black Star] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Resonance Link...
Playing the Soul's Melodies?
[Excalibur]
Worry not everyone...
I shall return...!
See you later!
[Black Star] You are so
unbearably lame!