[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Soul]
What is this place...?
Where am I?
Wherever it is,
it's completely dark...
I can't even see my own body.
It hurts.
[Soul]
Which way is up...?
Which way is down?
Where am I
supposed to go?
Someone help me.
Light...?
Is that a way out?
[Maka]
No...No, stop!
[Soul]
A voice...? Maka!
It's Maka's voice!
Wait there! I'm coming.
[Maka]
Soul!
[demented music playing]
[Maka screams]
[Soul and Maka scream]
[Maka]
Soul...! Soul!
What's the matter?
Good, Dr. Medusa...!
It's Soul.
[Soul slows down
screaming and breaths heavily]
Soul...
[Soul]
I'm all right.
I'll be okay...
I just had a bad
dream that's all.
That's good, Soul...
But if anything
does come up,
call me right away.
[Medusa thinks]
Ragnarok's black blood has
mixed in with Soul Eater's.
It looks like I may have
found myself a
new research subject.
♪ opening song ♪
[Maka]
All right then, Soul.
I'm going to head home.
Unless you need something.
Are you thirsty?
Do you want me to
get you a drink before I go?
[Soul] No,
don't worry about it...
What goes in
must come out,
and I'm not too crazy
about taking a leak in
these stupid bedpans.
Okay... Do you want me
to bring you anything
when I come back,
besides a change of underwear?
Nope, I can't think
of anything.
Okay.
Hey Maka...
I'm in this bed
because of something I did,
not because of you.
So don't get yourself all
worked up about it, okay?
Sorry.
[Soul thinks] Crap... I think I
just made her feel worse...
Way to go, Soul.
[Maka thinks] I'm an
idiot, letting my
emotions show like that?
It's not going to
do any good to get
Soul worried about me.
[footsteps]
[Maka]
Papa...?
Come up to the
roof with me...
We can watch the sun set.
Well... I'm here.
What am I supposed
to do now?
[Sid]
Clean...
Put the library back in order.
[Black Star]
Huh? No way, not me.
[Sid]
Listen, you brat...
...on your last
extracurricular lesson,
you didn't collect
a single soul.
[Black Star] Yeah,
well, that's what
remedial lessons
are for, right...?
I should know;
I've done enough of 'em lately.
What good will stacking
books do me...?
Cleaning...? No way...!
I'm too big for that...
Stars don't clean...
Isn't there anything
better for me to do?
Like when we beat up you
and the crazy professor?
Listen up for once,
Black Star...
You have more raw power
than almost anyone
else in your class.
And yet you have
nothing to show for it...
It isn't fair to Tsubaki.
She's trying hard,
and you're holding her back.
Right now, what you
need is punishment...
Something tedious and boring
to get you back on track.
[Black Star]
This is a huge mess.
Aren't you at least
gonna help me?
[Sid] That would
defeat the purpose...
I don't spoil my students.
That's not the
kind of man I was.
Great. What am
I gonna do now?
[Black Star howling
with laughter]
[Black Star] Charisma
Justice is awesome...!
He's almost as big
a star as I am...
I never knew they had
comic books in the library.
This is the kinda remedial
lesson that I can live with.
[Kid] Hey, keep it down,
would you...?
You're in a library.
Yeah, sorry.
[Black Star] What are
you doing here Kid...?
Are you being punished, too?
No, I'm here to
check out a book...
I'm conducting some
research into the symmetry
of famous weapons...
I'd actually like to take
that book that's under
your butt if you don't
mind moving for a second.
Oh... Right here?
What does the cover say?
[Black Star] E... eeks...
callee... burr?
Almost. Excalibur.
Yeah, what's that?
From what I've heard,
it's a legendary weapon.
Also known as
the Holy Sword.
[Kid] They say he who
draws the Holy Sword from
the ground will be
deemed a hero and
shall receive everlasting
glory and fame.
I've heard that someone
who obtained Excalibur
in the past went on to
become a mighty king.
I'll bet a sword as
powerful as this one
has absolutely
flawless symmetry...
Oh, symmetry!
Hero...! King...!
That sounds perfect to me!
Oh... You mean
Excalibur... huh?
Hey Professor, are you
here for punishment, too?
Punishment?
What're you talking
about, Black Star?
[Kid] Do you know anything
about the legend of Excalibur?
The Holy Sword Excalibur...
It was too much
even for me.
Really...?
You tried to pull the sword?
Even you couldn't
draw the sword, Professor...?
The Holy Sword Excalibur!
Now I'm really interested!
[Maka]
Legend of the Holy Sword...
~Kid and Black Star's
Great Adventure?~
[Death Scythe]
Look at that, Maka.
You see how ridiculous
the sun looks
trying to fight off sleep.
Pretty funny...
[Death Scythe thinks]
This isn't going well at all...
I finally have the
chance to talk to Maka
and I don't have a
clue what to talk about...
The way the sun looks
is a pretty lame topic.
(ah!)... She pulled out a book!
She's bored with me...!
I have to say something, quick!
Something clever,
something funny...
think... think...
(ugh) think faster, idiot!
Hey... You shouldn't be
reading in this light.
It's bad for your eyes.
Really...?!
Did I just start off
by lecturing her?!
Hey... Papa...
How do you feel
about Mama? Be honest.
[Death Scythe]
Don't show any hesitation.
That's easy.
I love her, of course.
Then how come you cheated
on her all the time?
[Death Scythe thinks] That was
way too much hesitation!
Now no matter what I say,
it won't sound convincing.
I'm in big trouble!
Hang in there...
Millions of men everywhere
are on your side.
Don't run away from this...
Stand and face your
daughter like a man...
Don't run, don't run,
don't run... don't run!
It's getting chilly,
don't you think...?
Maybe we should
head inside, huh?
Already...?
But we just got here.
[Death Scythe thinks]
I didn't run away quick enough!
All these pointed questions...
She's starting to take
after her mother.
Listen, Maka...
Papa loves you and Mama
more than anything
in the world...
...and that's the truth.
It's the truth...
It... is... the truth.
I swear it's the truth, Maka!
[Kid]
This is it.
[Black Star]
Yahoo!
Excalibur's up there
waiting for me.
Yes... According to this,
we'll have to climb up
there and find the
cave the sword is in.
[Black Star]
Hey...! No fair...!
Damn it...
Spoiled rich kids
have all the
best toys, don't they?
You're not
leaving me behind!
[Black Star starts
a rallying cry]
Kid's not here.
Where'd he go?
In there maybe?
[Kid]
Black Star...
I can't come down.
There's water... My pants
are going to get wet.
[Black Star] What are
you talking about?
You carry me.
Yeah, right...
You can stay there.
Such a terrible obstacle
so early in the quest...
Our chosen path...
is truly a cruel one.
Yeah, you've really got it
rough here, don't you?
I'll ward off the
water from above,
and you can handle the
water on the ground, okay...?
We'll work together.
It's a good thing there
are two of us here.
This way would
be impassible alone.
Quite an obstacle!
Dude, you're kind of a
useless idiot, aren't you?
Aah!
It looks like a fairy...
What's something like
that doing here?
We're hunting after
a legendary sword...
Finding a fairy or two
shouldn't be surprising...
Is Excalibur up ahead?
Are we in the right place?
She's not a very
polite fairy, is she?
Looks like the
path dead-ends here.
Hey... over there.
Yes... no doubt about it...
That's it...
The Holy Sword Excalibur.
Awesome!
The air here is vibrating.
Standing here I can easily
believe what the book says
about becoming a hero
and earning everlasting
fame and glory.
This cave certainly seems
like a magical place.
Just look at the sword.
Such precise, detailed
ornamentation on the hilt...
and not a single
nick on the blade.
This is indeed deserving
of the title "Holy Sword."
A magnificent sword,
which can only be pulled
out by the chosen hero.
By... me...
Yay! Looks like I'm a hero!
A big, big hero! Yahoo!
[Kid] This is some
kind of mistake...
I hate to break it to you,
but you're no hero.
How about a do-over?
Huh? You saying that
didn't count or something...?
Fine, but I'm sure it's just
gonna be the same every time.
No, this time I'm
going to do it.
Yeah right. You wish...
The sword chose me
to be its hero, Kid...
I'm a big, fat hero!
Best to be safe.
Who knows who else has touched
this sword over the years?
Hurry up and do it.
It came out!
Huh?! How come you
were able to get it out, too?
It must be because
I loosened it.
[Excalibur]
Welcome...
Welcome to my cave,
young ones.
It's talking!
[Excalibur] Please forgive the
belated salutations...
I am the Holy Sword...
...Excalibur!
How... incredibly...
...lame.
[Death Scythe makes childish
gibberish sounds]
Papa... Would you tell me
more about the Demon Sword...
...Ragnarok?
Long ago...
...meisters and weapons
worked together under
Lord Death to maintain
peace and order in the world,
the same function for
which you are being trained.
No meister and weapon
pair was allowed to
collect the soul of a
human being for
any reason whatsoever.
That rule still stands...
and now it seems as
natural to us as breathing.
Because while a human
soul increases a weapon's
ability and power just
as a Kishin soul does,
the price is steep...
A weapon that takes a
human soul will pay by
losing his or her
own human heart.
[Death Scythe continues]
Despite the risk, however...
...there were meisters who
broke that sacred rule.
These meisters feared
death above all else...
Their constant battles
left them frightened...
broken... and they took to
hunting human souls.
Again and again,
they defied the rule,
secretly feeding their
weapons the souls
of innocent humans.
As a result...
...a Kishin was born
into this world.
[Death Scythe] Death Weapon
Meister Academy was founded in
order to recover souls who
have left the human path and
become eggs of Kishin...
It was also created to
train and oversee meisters
and weapons who are
too young to hunt down evil
without someone to guide them.
The ultimate goal is to
prevent the Kishin from
ever being reborn and
once again raining terror
down upon the world.
[Maka]
So... the Demon Sword...
[Death Scythe] Yes...
It devours human souls...
It was melted down by a
witch and implanted in
the body of a
meister as black blood.
Now... The Demon Sword...
...Ragnarok is only one step
away from becoming a Kishin.
And it's not just the
sword we have
to worry about...
There are people who
could become Kishin as well.
And beyond that...
There's Soul...
...whose body now
contains black blood.
Let's see...
Are you still hard at work
like a good boy, Black Star?
Ooh! See what you
can do if you
put your mind to it!
(oh) Hi, Professor Sid...
After I put this book away,
I'll be all done.
Tsubaki?! So, that sneaky
little brat dumped his
punishment on her
and took off, did he?
Back when I was still alive,
I hated it when dirty tricks
like this were pulled!
[Tsubaki] It's okay Professor,
don't worry about it...
I enjoy cleaning.
If you're looking
for Black Star,
he's not here.
He and Kid went to
find the Holy Sword...
Why has he done
something wrong?
[Sid]
The... Holy Sword.
Yes... Excalibur.
The same sword...
that tears the air...
...and shakes the very ground?
Let's stop talking about it.
Yeah... in some way,
this is the ultimate
remedial lesson.
I'll let this one slide...
That's the kind of man I was.
Okay... I've got a bunch of
tests that need grading.
[Tsubaki]
Huh?
[Black Star]
You're the Holy Sword...?
In the top hat?!
Seriously?!
[Kid snickers]
[Excalibur] You're one to talk,
in that funny outfit...!
Who are you, exactly?
Who am I...?
I'm Black Star, the bi--
[Excalibur] My legend dates back
to the twelfth century,
thank you very much...
From the looks of you,
you must be meisters...
Where are you children from?
Who do you think you are,
pointing that thing at me...?
Put it down freak.
We're from Death Weapon Meis--
[Excalibur] I know that. Here,
I want to show you something.
Then why did you ask if
you already knew the answer?
[Black Star]
What's with this guy...?
And why the hell isn't
he wearing any pants?
What's he showing us, I wonder.
[Excalibur] Young ones, do you
want to hear the legend of me?
[Black Star]
Put that thing away!
[Excalibur] Do you want to
hear a heroic tale?
Get that out of my face!
[Excalibur] Where have you
traveled here from?
[Black Star]
Like we said!
We're from
Death Weapon Meister--
[Excalibur] What is
your favorite number
between 1 and 12?
[Black Star]
What...?
Between 1 and 12?
One, obviously, cuz I refuse to
back down until I'm number one.
And mine is eight...
...because of its
perfect symmetry.
[Excalibur] Fools...! What right
do you have to choose a number?
My legend dates all the
way back to the twelfth century,
you know.
You asked us to pick a
favorite number, so we did!
[Excalibur] Do you want to
hear my legend or not?
Just quit with the
cane already, will ya?
[Excalibur]
As I said...
...my legend begins
in the twelfth century.
My mornings begin
with a cup of coffee
with cream at the café.
My afternoons begin
with a cup of hot tea
with two lumps of sugar.
And my evenings--
Let me guess, booze...?
Sounds right for
an old guy like you.
[Excalibur]
Fool!
In the evening,
I change into my pajamas.
Why do we
care about that?
That's all irrelevant
to the legend...
Besides, pajamas---
[Excalibur] Fools...! Do you
know what this hat is?
Huh?
[Excalibur]
I asked...
...do you know
what this hat is?
How should we know that?
It appears to be
made of silk,
if that's what you mean.
[Excalibur]
Fools...! If you don't know,
I guess I'll have to tell you...
The taller the chef's hat,
the greater the chef.
Okay, so what you're
trying to tell
us then is you're--
[Excalibur] Fool!
Who said that I was a chef ?
Dude, nothing you're
saying makes any sense!
[Excalibur] This is why
I can't abide hayseeds.
AHHHH!
You are beyond annoying!
Black Star calm down...
Don't let this guy and
his nonsense get to you.
'Holy Sword',
you gotta be kidding me!
Let me see that book!
It's completely unreliable!
Who wrote this...?
Let's see... the author is...
Eee...eks, cal,
ee...mmm....bur?
[Kid]
Excalibur.
It was you?!
[Excalibur]
No autographs.
Professor...?
I have a question.
What kind of weapon
is the Holy Sword?
Oh...that, huh?
Whoever draws the sword
is said to be
made a great king,
given wings of light,
and granted the ability
to soar through the sky...
The sword can cut through
space with a single swing...
Without a doubt;
it is the most powerful
weapon in the world.
I see... but only a hero
who's been chosen can
match soul wavelengths
with it, right?
No... that's not true,
unfortunately.
[Stein]
Surprisingly enough,
Excalibur can
match with anyone.
[Excalibur] Before becoming
my meister, there is a list of a
thousand provisions
you must peruse.
Be sure to look
through all of them.
They're important.
Even the backs of these
pages have been written on.
[Excalibur] I greatly look
forward to your participation in
number four-hundred-and
fifty-two...
the five hour
storytelling party.
And thus...
Thus, you have
been chosen.
It shall all be yours...!
Victory... and glory!
Victory!
Glory!
[Excalibur]
Now, let's go! Together!
Yeah, right...who'd ever
want a sword like you?
Useless piece of metal.
Anybody can match their
soul wavelength with
the sword just fine,
but there's no one in
the world who can ever
match personal wavelengths
with Excalibur.
[Excalibur] Hey...
Hold on...! Come back!
I'll tell you what...
I can lower those one thousand
provisions down
to eight hundred.
Just as long as you
take part in the
story telling party!
[Black Star] Anyone who can put
up with him is a hero.
[Kid]
Disgusting!
Oh hi!
Did you meet the
Holy Sword Excalibur?
[Fairy]
Yeah, they met him.
[bells toll]
[Black Star] We've both got
fine partners already, huh?
[Kid]
Mm hmm.
[Liz and Patty]
Hmm?
[Soul] All right...! It looks
like the gang is all here.
[All]
Hey Soul!
So, are you
all fixed up now?
The real party can't get
started without you around.
Yeah...
I'm a lot better.
[girls giggling]
Do you hear that,
Black Star...?
I'm starting to get the
strange feeling that
other people have
been laughing at us.
[Student A]
Those two?
[Student B]
They're the ones?
[Student C]
Yeah, it's for them.
Hey, Black Star,
Kid, c'mere...
I think you'd better see this...
[Black Star and Kid]
Is he serious?
What is that thing?
Don't know...it's intense.
Top hat freak.
Disgusting.
♪ ending song ♪
[Excalibur] You want to hear
my legend, don't you?
[Maka] Wow, you're amazing...
amazingly lame!
[Excalibur]
Fool!
[Maka] Really...?
I don't think I'm the fool here.
Anyway, next time,
Tsubaki and Black Star
challenge the Enchanted Sword.
[Excalibur]
Fool!
[Maka]
Okay, okay, you're right.
I'm a fool.
[Excalibur]
Fool!
[Maka]
Yep, you're right. I know.
[Excalibur]
Fool!
[Maka]
Shut up, you freak.
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Enchanted Sword Masumune...
Break the Soul Possession:
A Heart Sings in the Rain?
[Excalibur]
Fool!
[Maka]
You're so annoying!