[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Kid]
Lost Island...
Long ago an explosion
occurred here,
creating a dangerously
strong magnetic field.
Now, the island is the site
of a battle between the
DWMA and Arachnophobia.
While members of both sides
struggled for possession of
the Magic Tool Brew,
three of us entered the magnetic
field with our weapons in search
of Professor Stein
and Miss Marie.
Waiting for us inside the field
was a scene from the past...
...frozen in time by
that long ago explosion.
♪ opening song ♪
[Ox]
Die!
[Kilik] Damn it...
They just keep on coming.
Now what?
We've almost reached the
twenty minute mark.
It's time, Kim...
Give the signal for retreat.
We'll watch your back.
Okay. Make sure I'm covered...
You ready, Jackie?
[Jacqueline]
Yeah.
[Kilik] They're attacking
in force again!
Let's go!
I got it!
Resonance Link!
[Jacqueline]
Change... Pixie!
[Kilik]
I don't think so!
[Ox]
Royal Thunder!
Flash of Lightning!
[Kilik and Ox]
Thunder Combination!
Good job, you guys. Thanks...!
Okay, now it's our turn Jackie!
[Maka]
Mosquito's Storm!
o~Ten Minutes to Fight
in the World of the Past?
Where are they hiding?
[Naigus] Confirmed.
Target sighted.
Welcome...
We have plans for you.
[Naigus]
One more step...
Now.
That's gunpowder.
[Naigus]
Spikes!
Alright Naigus...
I've got him... Do it!
Now!
Die!
I get it now...
If all teachers at the
academy are like you,
I can see how Black Star
became the fighter he is.
You're a true
professional, samurai...
I can respect that.
What I don't get...
...is why you'd work for
an organization
like Arachnophobia.
It's such a waste.
That signal...!
An order to retreat?
It's over...
We're being called off.
I have no more reason
to attack you now...
You can put down
your sword and end this.
What'll it be?
Of course...
it might be safer
to finish me...
If we do meet up again,
you may not be able to escape.
[Mifune]
I'll take that chance.
Go on.
[random soldier]
All troops: withdraw...!
Withdraw!
[Stein laughs insanely]
What's wrong?
Can you hear me...?
What's happening?!
[Stein laughs insanely]
[Stein]
I'm drowning...
The madness has me.
You need to get a
hold of yourself, Franken!
[Stein]
Madness.
Why is this happening now?!
It's like there's something
eating him from the inside out.
[Stein] You have
to watch me, Marie...
There's no telling
what I might do.
[Black Star]
Here they are.
We've been looking all
over for you guys...
Are you all right?
You three...?
What do you think
you're doing here?
I told you to stay out...
You disobeyed me.
It's been twenty minutes
since you came in here...
You need to get out.
[Marie] His body
is beginning to blur.
What about Brew?
We haven't been in long.
It'll still be safe
for ten minutes...
We can look for the tool.
Let's go!
Hurry and get out!
Hey, hold it...!
Get back here now!
I can't chase after them.
We have to get out...
But when we get back,
they're in big trouble.
[Black Star]
We already disobeyed orders.
We might as well go all the way.
Where is this thing anyway?
Disobeying orders...!
What am I turning into?
[Kid]
There's a gate up ahead...
Someone's there.
Is he part of the past?
It seems like he noticed us...
He looks familiar.
I think I've seen him
somewhere before.
[Maka] Could that box he's got
be what we're looking for?
I expected to run into
academy agents, but I didn't
think they'd send three meisters
fresh from their playpens.
All you have to do is
hand over the box you're
carrying, old man...
Do that and you
can be on your way.
Old man, huh?
Don't underestimate me...
Little brat.
Consider my offer...
Have you looked
at your body lately?
My body?
You're beginning to blur...
You can't afford to stay
in the field much longer...
We've still got ten
minutes left, though...
We won't even
have to fight you.
You'll become a
memory before long...
All we have to do is
prevent you from
leaving the magnetic field...
...and the rest will be
taken care of for us.
That's true...
This old body can't handle
more than twenty
minutes in here.
It's all right, though...
That can be fixed...
Shaving off a few years
should give me plenty of time.
Four hundred perhaps?
No, no...
One hundred should be enough.
[Mosquito chants]
Go ahead! Call me old now...!
This is how I looked
one hundred years ago.
This body should buy
me an extra ten minutes...
So now we're even.
Eww... His torso inflated so
much that his legs
are dangling in the air...
Does that look right to you?
None of it looks right to me.
Not really an improvement.
You three look quite tasty...
I bet you have
delicious young blood.
Who is this guy...?
Another memory...?
Just when things were
about to get interesting, too.
[Maka]
We should be careful.
He's here...
Eibon.
What did you just say?!
[Kid]
Is that really... Eibon?
[Maka]
Do you recognize him Kid?
[Kid]
Uh... no...
Time's running out, guys.
We're down to less
than ten minutes here...
We can't afford to
mess around anymore.
Let's get 'im!
Hand it over, gramps.
I may not know exactly
what's going on here,
but I know that tool is ours!
Eibon's getting away...!
C'mon Black Star!
[Black Star]
No time for that, Kid...
This show's ending
in ten minutes...
We've gotta prioritize.
Ten minutes is barely enough
time for a star like me
to put in a decent appearance.
You're pathetic!
You think making yourself
a few years younger and
a few pounds heavier
is gonna help against me?!
Don't make me laugh!
Hey!
Black Star's actually
right this time.
Our first priority is
getting Brew... Let's go.
[Maka]
Right!
Careful...! Are you guys okay?
Wake up, Kid!
Right, I know...
We've gotta take
care of this guy first.
Clearly, this man lacks
any sense of symmetry...
Let's remedy that.
Right...!
That's the spirit, Kid!
Three little babies...
This is all you're capable of?
[Mosquito] They don't make
'em like they used to.
This was me a hundred years ago.
Tougher and stronger than
all three of you put together.
[Maka]
No way...
There isn't a
single scratch on him.
This is bad...
We can't resonate souls
as a team, not in this place.
The static's too loud...
Maka's the only one
who could do it...
Her ability to perceive souls
is strong enough for this.
What are we gonna do, Soul...?
We'll never beat him if
we can't use resonance link.
[Soul]
Maybe I could direct her
ability and channel
everyone's souls.
What do you mean 'maybe'?
You know you
can do it.... Don't you...
Evans?
Don't call me
by that name, dammit.
Come on... right this way.
We're set up and ready to
go for the big concert.
[Sid]
Look after the injured.
[Naigus] The battle
didn't go our way.
You should look
after your injury, too.
I will... Soon enough.
Sid! Naigus!
We're here!
Kim, Jacqueline...
Glad you made it...
What about the others?
Well, sir...
The teachers
never came back out...
So Maka's team
went in to find them...
Ox and Kilik are
holding back the enemy.
They did what...?! Azusa...
Can you find the students?
No, I'm afraid not...
The field is too strong.
I can't see them.
[Sid] It'll take fifteen minutes
to get there in this snow...
Azusa, gather ten people who
can make the trek with me.
[Naigus]
Sid...
[Azusa] With those
injuries, you shouldn't!
Naigus... Quickly
see to my injuries.
[Naigus]
All right.
[Ox]
After the first wave,
our technique
suffered a little bit.
The enemy was rather strong,
but still, we could've
done much better.
Who cares if we
were a little sloppy...?
We won the fight, didn't we?
[Kilik]
Professor! Miss Marie!
What happened in there?!
I need you to watch
over the Professor.
[Stein] What are
you planning, Marie...?
The effects of the field won't
disappear just because you
stepped out of it for a moment.
Go back in and you're
throwing your life away.
I know that!
But if I don't,
what will happen?
You mean the rest
of them are still inside?
Then let us go in after them.
No...! You're not
going anywhere...!
I'm not letting any more of
my students go inside
that death trap!
If you disobey orders,
you will be punished...
I'll expel you!
What are we gonna do now Ox...?
You can't get expelled
from the academy.
[Ox] I don't think we have much
choice in the matter, Harvar.
None at all.
Academy students protect
their own. Simple as that.
[Marie]
No... Wait!
[Marie] Expulsion...
I can't even do that.
They don't let brand new
teachers go around
expelling students...
Not that threatening to stopped
them from going, anyway.
I'm an adult...
I'm their teacher...
I can't do anything!
What do I do...? I let them go!
What if they never come back?
[Marie sobs]
[Stein]
Don't cry, Marie.
The failure of the mission...
...any harm that comes
to the students...
Everything... it's all my fault.
All of it!
[Stein laughs like a mad man]
All!
[Mosquito] Surely
you've realized by now
that you can't beat me.
Shut up...! Give us
Brew immediately!
You think you're such
smart little children.
Can you even tell me what
this Magic Tool
inside my hat does?
Of course you can't...
And yet you've come all
this way and fought so
hard to get your hands on it...
The folly of youth has no end.
You brats don't even know
what you're fighting for.
We have Brew now...
Arachnophobia will soon
control the entire world.
You should run while you can.
[Black Star]
Shut up, grandpa...
I'm tired of hearing you yammer.
Tsubaki...! Enchanted Sword!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
Magic Tool...?
Who cares about that...?
Not me, baldy.
This isn't a fight between
Arachnophobia and the academy.
Not anymore...
It's between me and you!
Maka, Kid...!
Follow my lead on this!
Shadow Star!
A puny attack like that's not
going to do any damage
to me, you foolish boy!
Maka!
You bastard!
That was only round one.
I'll still take you down!
At this rate,
we've got no chance!
I'm growing bored.
Time to get rid of you.
Had enough yet?
A little more?
Tiny bugs like you
are easy to crush.
Come on guys!
It's time to get up now!
Shall we pull the curtain
down on this sad play?
No, the show's just beginning...
Right, Soul...?
Let's get started.
Police Stinger!
There's no more
time to think about it...
The stage is all set for the
big concert. It's time to play.
[Soul] The black blood
already spread to Maka...
This'll spread it to everyone
else on the team, won't it?
[Li'l Demon] Your
resonance with them
will be an indirect
connection...
The blood won't spread if you
don't resonate
strongly with Maka.
Come with me now...
...to the Black Room.
Let your souls sing
together in sweet harmony...
While the black blood runs
faster and stronger
throughout your veins.
[Soul]
I know I have to...
But do I have it in me?
[Soul]
The piano will play...
And the madness
will dance to the tune.
What do I do?
[Soul]
Listen, everyone...
We're going to
resonate as a team...
Using sound.
Using sound...?
But Soul do you even
know how to do
something like that?
I think so...
I thought of it a while ago,
back when we
first learned about
linking souls together.
Here's how it works...
Our wavelengths
communicate through Maka.
That's possible even here since
her soul perception
is so strong.
I still don't see how
we're supposed to resonate.
[Soul] I'll play the
piano with my soul.
The sound will resonate
directly with your
soul wavelengths.
[group laughs]
I don't get it...
Why's everyone laughing?
It's just that...
We've been trying
to come up with a plan...
...you never want to play...
So we were going
to trick you into it.
And now you're
offering to do it.
Unfortunately, we can only
stay in here for
five more minutes...
So the concert
will be a bit rushed.
Please play for us, Soul...
We're ready.
We've been looking
forward to this for awhile.
Yep!
What do you think?
Good crowd tonight.
[Li'l Demon]
Everything's in place...
The piano's all tuned up
and ready to be played.
[Soul]
That so?
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] I haven't heard Soul
play in a long time.
[Black Star] It'll be funny
if he messes up.
[Maka]
Button your shirt...!
Sit up straight...!
Hands in your lap!
[Black Star] Hey!
I'm not the one performing!
[Maka] Even audience members
should have manners...!
Look! Soul's about to begin!
[Black Star] All right,
let's hear it...!
Play to my soul, Soul...!
Uh... did I miss anything?
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Unleash the Seven's
Chain Resonance
A Recital of
Destruction and Creation?o~
[Maka] Watch it,
or I'll take your soul!