A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
You've already done everything
you need to do here...
There's no reason
for you to stay.
Medusa wants you to join
her now to help with
some other tasks she
has in mind for you.
But... I don't wanna leave...
I wanna stay right here.
Personally, I don't care
one way or the other.
I just pass along
information...
But I can't say that Medusa
will feel the same way.
This is the first time
I've ever had friends...
If I leave, I won't be able
to see them anymore.
Your whining is giving
me a headache!
Just do what Medusa
tells you to, idiot...
Sooner or later everyone
here will find out what you did.
Or have you already forgotten
the snake you planted in
Marie to accelerate the
pace of Stein's madness?
When they know about that,
there's no way you're going to
get off with a
Reaper Chop or two!
And you know that won't be it.
Just think how Maka will feel.
She'll probably cry.
Don't you see it's over?
Nothing you can do now will
change the fact that
you betrayed them all.
♪ opening song ♪
Wake up...! Get out here!
We came a long way
to get here...!
The least you can do is invite
us in and offer us a drink!
Are you finished?
Huh?
That's the Kishin in there...
You can yell and complain
all you want, it won't bother
him more than a buzzing fly.
Well maybe he'd rather hear
the screaming of a mosquito.
Looking for a fight, old man?
Lady Arachne! Please wait...!
Let us go in first!
You can stay out there.
I'll handle this alone.
Lady Arachne.
Crona's Escape... Show Me
Your Smile, Please?o~
Greetings Kishin Asura...
I am Lady Arachne.
I know your great power
and respect it...
I have journeyed
far to meet you...
Will you not show me your face?
I've heard others say you hide
here because you're timid.
But I suspect you came to this
isolated mountain to rejuvenate
your soul. Am I correct?
Perhaps I'm wrong...
Perhaps you're as afraid of
the Grim Reaper as they say.
I grow weary of hide and seek.
Please come out.
Go away.
Are you this intimidated by a
lone woman? That's almost cute.
I found you.
I've been looking forward
to this moment.
What are you planning...? What
is it you want with me, woman?
The Reaper has stood
in my way long enough.
I want you to help
me eliminate him.
I've hated him for
eight hundred years.
I loathe him more
now than ever...
You understand how that
feels. I know you do.
If we don't join forces,
we'll both fall to him again.
Is that what you want?
To be tied up in a sack
of your own skin again?
Fight with me...
Together we'll be so strong
nothing can hurt us...
We'll protect each other.
I'll give it all to you... Don't
you see what I'm offering?
My heart... my soul. All of it.
Is yours to claim.
Yummy!
Hey, Crona, you should
practice with us the next
time we work on
resonance link...
It's fun, and I know you'd add
a lot of strength to our team.
Oh...Uh... yeah...
And I'll be there, so you'll be
trained by the best of the
best. You can't beat that!
Have another sandwich,
Crona. There's plenty.
Thanks.
You may be ugly,
but your food is delicious!
Actually, I can't take credit
for the food this time...
It was a special treat
from Miss Marie.
I'm sure taking care of
Professor Stein is pretty hard
on her but somehow she still
makes time to take care of us.
I'm gonna kill whoever did this
to the professor... Of course,
I'll have to eat first to
build up my strength.
Hey...! Why don't we go visit
the professor...?
I'm sure he'd love to see
you... What do you say, Crona?
Do you want to come along?
I...I... I have to
use the restroom!
You can do that by
yourself. I'm staying here...
Hey! There's still food to eat!
Where're you going?
I wanna stay with the food!
That's weird even for him.
It's impossible... How could
I ever tell them what I did?
Ragnarok was
right. I can't stay.
I don't belong here anymore.
You're such an
obedient child, Crona.
You finally see the
truth, don't you?
You don't fit in
here, not really...
The only place you'll
ever belong is with me.
Lady Medusa...
You should be more careful.
This belongs in a frame,
not on the ground.
Oh, yeah...
Uh, Maka?
Do... um... do you think
I could ask you something.
Of course... Ask me anything.
I, um... I was wondering
about your mother.
Oh. It's complicated.
She's sort of missing right now.
Wait hold on... What do
you mean missing?
Well... occasionally she'll
send me a postcard.
So I know she's off somewhere
traveling around the world,
but I don't really know where
she is or what she's doing.
She abandoned her daughter
to go on some trip...?
Who would do
something like that?
So... what...
What kind of person is she?
She's like a grizzly bear.
A... grizzly bear?
She's strong... hot-tempered...
You don't want to see
her when she's angry.
But she's still warm and
kind-hearted and loyal.
That seems like a lot of things
for one person to be...
So... um... Tell me some
more. What's the best memory
you have from when you
were younger, of her?
That's easy...
Definitely the divorce.
Huh?!
She was so cool and collected...
It was pretty amazing.
What a weird answer... Maka's
got a strange family life.
What's wrong...? Did I say
something odd?
Oh...! No...
I know that-- I know
she's not around now,
but how do you feel about her?
She's my mom, silly. I love her.
Didn't you say you had
to use the restroom?
Yeah.
I'll need five hundred
tons of concrete
and two hundred
tons of I-beams.
Also thirty thousand
bearings with
a five hundred
millimeter diameter...
...you think you
can make that happen?
Why do you need all that?
Are you planning to
build a skyscraper?
Whether it's fixing leaky pipes
or constructing a building...
if Lord Death asks me
to do something, I'll do it.
How obedient of you.
Hey I forgot to
tell you something.
If you see Uncle Bob
from the coffee shop
I need you to let me know...
It's very important. I can't
dance without my Rumba coffee.
I forgot to tell you
something, too.
You should get some new shoes.
Sandals aren't safe
for construction.
Does he have no respect for
a man's personal
taste in footwear?
Joe Buttataki.
He's a hard man to grasp...
Like the steam rising
from his coffee cup...
I find him unsettling.
He reminds me too
much of my father.
Unwilling to reveal
his secrets...
Always hiding behind a mask...
Not telling anyone what
his true intentions are.
There...! That's much better.
What the hell is going on down
here?! This is unacceptable.
Who could perpetrate
such a horror?!
And there he goes.
We've lost him again.
Hey, wait!
Where did he go?!
Quit it, Patty!
This Kid is becoming
troublesome.
Why's he so persistent...?
He should just relax with
a good cup of coffee.
It was like this
when I got here...
Empty. No belongings. No Crona.
He probably ran away.
But why would he do that?
He's been acting
strange lately.
Don't tell me you haven't
noticed... Distant.
Scared all the time.
It almost seemed like he didn't
want to hang around
with us anymore...
Admit it... You sensed it too.
At any rate, Lord Death
will find out he's
gone sooner or later.
And he won't be pleased.
I'll find him.
Hey, Maka...
Just like her...Running
off after him
without a thought in her head.
Crona... Why...? Why'd you go?
Where are you?
Why now...? I don't understand.
Everyone thinks you ran away,
but they're wrong...
aren't they?
I don't know why
you're so bummed.
Just think, we never have to
look at their ugly
faces again...!
Give it a little while.
Once you get home,
you'll forget all about
the stupid academy.
I don't think so. I'm not
going back to Medusa.
Huh?!
I can't stay at the academy,
and I can't go home.
I just want to be alone.
A weakling like you...?
You won't last two
days on your own...
What are you going
to do for food...?
If you're not going
to Medusa's,
you might as well turn around
and go back to the academy!
Get off of me...! There's no
way I can go back there!
--Stupid kid. What, are you
doing, trying to starve me...?
--I couldn't stand them
being so nice to
--I'm not gonna die
in the desert with you.
--me after I betrayed them.
It was breaking my heart.
--You don't know anything,
you useless pansy!
--Stop it! That hurts...!. Get
off me...! Get off m--
Please forgive me, Lady Arachne!
You must be in so much pain...!
That should never have
happened while I was with you...
It's all my fault...!
Please, please forgive me!
We succeeded in recruiting
the Kishin to our side.
This is a time to
celebrate, not to cry.
Yes... my lady.
Well, it wasn't
easy, but I did it.
Our new Kishin friend's
been given the best
bedroom we had available.
He even had a little snack on
the way... three of our men.
He's like a dog being
introduced to its
new owner for the first time.
He'll be suspicious
of us at first.
Tasty.
How long are we going to
stay in this hole...?
I'm baking in this sun!
I found a place where I can
be alone, like I wanted...
I'll stay here until
I'm ready to leave.
I've been somewhere
like this before...
A lonely place without water.
That's where we met. My first
lonely place in the desert.
Will you let me be
your friend Crona?
It was like feeling
sunlight for the first time.
But we were as different
as night and day...
How could I ever let myself
imagine our friendship
would last?
It was a nice dream, I guess...
...but it would be better
if I could forget it.
Crona!
You're sure this
is the right spot?
Yeah... I'm positive.
I can feel his soul nearby.
Crona!
Maka.
Stop here, Soul!
Crona! I finally found you!
And let's get you
out of there...
Hey, Soul...! Gimme a hand!
Why did you come after me?
You can leave me alone...
I didn't ask for your help.
Go away! I said, go away!
Why, Crona?
I don't want you here. You don't
understand anything about me...
Go...! Just get out of here!
I... I can't look at you...
not after... what I did.
The... the things that have been
happening to Professor Stein...
...those...those are all
because of me...
It was in Miss
Marie's drink... I...
I put one of Lady Medusa's
special little snakes in it.
Miss Marie never even
suspected me for a second.
She liked me... She kept telling
me what a good kid I was.
Why'd she do that? I never
asked her to be nice to me...!
Having faith in other people...
Trusting someone
not to hurt you...
How idiotic is that...?!
You know?!
Stop... Don't move...
Not another word.
Maka...? Hey!
Don't you dare say one more
negative thing about yourself.
You think of yourself as someone
who is cowardly and weak...
...yet, whenever
something happens,
you put everyone else first.
And then...You end up getting
hurt... Please stop this...
You're hurting my friend,
and I can't take it.
Please tell me I'm right?!
No... I... I can't say it.
I hate this so much...
but there's nothing I can do...!
I'm so tired of all
of this... When...?
...can I stop... hur--
hurting people...? I...
I don't wanna hurt
anybody...! I don't wanna
make people sad! I don't
wanna lose my only friend!
You see? I am a coward, like
I said. And... and I might...
...end up betraying you again!
I won't let that happen...
I promise, I won't!
What do you say...?
Can we go home?
Have they realized
they're in a big hole yet?
I suppose they're expecting
me to dig them out of there...
Not cool. Not even
a little bit cool.
Hmm... I understand
your loyalty to your friend...
...but Crona did sign
the academy agreement.
Students who break the
rules are expelled...
That's the way it works...
Making an exception for him
would undermine the stability
of the entire academy.
It can't be done.
Crona knows he was wrong.
He already apologized
for what he did...
He feels awful about all of it!
Maka... this problem can't be
solved by saying sorry.
What Crona did
was extremely serious.
You're a fine one
to talk about loyalty.
You don't know what loyalty is!
How many promises did you break
when you and Mom
were together?!
How many times did you say
'sorry' only to do it again?!
Those two situations
have nothing in common.
Don't you understand
the gravity of this?
No, I don't!
If you got a second chance,
so should he.
I trust him not to do it again.
Hmmm...
Lord Death...!
An urgent police report!
Someone's been
sighted in the city!
"Someone" being...?
The snake woman has come back.
It's Medusa.
Why have you come here?
I'm not here to fight you.
I surrender.
♪ closing music ♪
Wow, that was a really
good episode, wasn't it, Sis?
I guess...
If you're sentimental.
That part at the end was
so sweet it made me cry!
I suppose it was
a little touching.
It looks like it even
made you cry, big sis!
I'm not crying. I don't know
what you're talking about.
But your face is wet,
and your eyes are all puffy!
Uh...
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Cards Are Cut... Medusa
Surrenders to The DWMA?o~
I told you, I wasn't crying!