A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
The path of the warrior
or the path of the demon.
Think hard, Black Star.
You still have a chance
to choose the right path.
Shut up, samurai...
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You've chosen the demon.
I can do nothing more for you.
Black Star!!
Where am I?
What the--!
Let go!
Let go!!
Noooo!!!
What am I seeing?
♪ opening song ♪
Hey, Free...
can you hear me?
Yeah...
loud and clear.
Our line to Medusa has
been cut off for awhile...
I think that might mean...
She's dead, right?
Probably so...
What do you think, Mizune?
Right...
which means...
Yeah, time to bail out.
Is something wrong, Ox?
Uh... no...
Then let's keep moving!
Right...
The Miraculous
Coffee Table Flip...
Fly, Our Death City Robot?
Brew...
Unlock.
It begins.
What's it doing?
It's getting bigger and bigger!
Look closely, everyone...
This is Eibon's
ultimate creation.
The Magic Tool Brew
is assuming its true form.
Lord Death...
The tool is ready.
Thank you, Eibon.
Dad... what exactly
is Brew's power?
What does it do?
Brew is a unique device...
Its power lies in
its ability to take
whatever form its
wielder most desires.
How is that possible?
It becomes tuned
to the wielder's soul...
Brew measures the strength
of that soul's desire...
...and alters itself
accordingly.
And therein lies its
most fearsome power...
If used the wrong way, Brew
could destroy the entire world.
Brew's power terrified
even its creator...
To protect it from falling
into the wrong hands,
he locked the device and bound
his own soul to the key.
Which means...
...the key to the Magic Tool...
...is Eibon's soul itself...
Without the presence
of its creator...
Brew's power can
never be activated.
Lord Death...
as you predicted,
my research led to nothing but
grief and sorrow in the end.
The death of friendship...
Betrayal...
involvement with witches.
And the loss of
the one I loved most.
But now at least...
I can make amends for my
misdeeds by helping you.
Do you remember
what you said to me...
...all those years ago?
Even if you
triumph over death...
...you'll find nothing
but grief and sorrow.
For the first time...
...I understand what you meant.
Eibon...
Save the world.
Fool!
Lord Death...
do you copy?
We have a situation...
The enemy has a new weapon.
At this rate, we can't
hold on much longer!
Looks like we're gonna
need to speed things up a bit.
I never seem to know what
to say in situations like this.
But you just said
something, didn't you?
That's true, I did...
Okay...
I'll shut up.
Yeah...
so will I.
The tool takes the form
of its wielder's desire...
What will it become
for my father?
All right...!
Let's get this
party started, shall we?
What's happening?
Dad?!
Death City is moving!
So, you've shown up again.
Why are you here...?
Well...?
What, are you trying to get
back into my good graces?
I'm here to bid you farewell.
What?
Don't you understand?
Understand what?
That you've finally lost.
Oh, yeah?
Even now...
you are surrounded by warriors
who have lost the
will to survive...
Soon they'll devour you.
You are deep inside
the Enchanted Sword...
This is the final
destination for those
whose souls have been
irrevocably shattered by fear.
What I saw...
Those images from earlier...
Farewell, weakling...
We shall not meet again.
You bragged that you
would surpass God...
Instead, look where
you've ended up.
Hold it...
We aren't done.
Black Star...
You're lost in a
world of darkness...
Soon, it will swallow your soul
and you'll be gone forever.
All I can hope for you
is a peaceful end.
I suppose you're
not lost after all.
You chose the
path of the warrior.
Path of the warrior?
What's this?
You will never see my tears.
You get it...?
These tears belong to
those fallen soldiers.
I'll save them from
their fear and sorrow...
I will take up their burdens.
Foolish boy!
I told you,
you've already lost...
Despair is all
that remains for you...
...and you can
never change that.
That's where you're wrong!
I haven't lost anything...
I don't run from fear...
I stand and face it.
The day I lose
will be the day I die.
I won't be devoured,
and I won't give up...
You will never defeat me!
You're going to fight
for the fallen warriors...?
Those left behind on the path?
Nakatsukasa...
I'm going to show
you a new world.
Like none you've ever seen!
My family's souls...
We're all with you now.
Mifune...
let's get something straight...
The path I choose isn't that of
the warrior or the demon...
You don't know this path...
You've never seen
it before, samurai.
My path...! And nobody
else's you GOT me!
You reject warrior and demon...
...and choose a path
of your own making.
Let's see it...
Show me this path.
Mifune.
Go on, then...
One stroke will finish me.
You're giving up samurai...?
Already?
Isn't there somebody you're
still sworn to protect...?
And don't forget...
Tsubaki made you a pretty
good offer the last time we met.
You care about helping children,
and you have incredible skill...
You'd fit in well
at the academy...
Why not become
a teacher instead?
What...?
A teacher at the academy?
You coming?
Don't worry...
...we'll find that little
witch of yours first.
Mosquito's putting up a
better fight than I expected.
That's interesting, I would've
thought you'd be a bit upset.
What? Why?!
Come now...
...surely you've noticed
what's been happening.
Spit it out already!
What're you talking about?!
They've been attacking
indiscriminately...
In other words, Arachnophobia
doesn't care if you die.
What the hell...?!
Seriously?!
Seriously.
Damn that witch!
There's no hope for you now...
Lady Arachne planned well...
We just sacrifice some
of our own forces...
...and in doing so, we ensure
that victory will be ours.
Next target sighted!
This is it...
This is where we die.
Fire!!!
What the--?!
What is that?
What the heck is that?!
Phew!
We made it...
but just barely.
What...
...is that?
This was Dad's wish.
All those years ago, he bound
his soul to Death City
in order to seal
the Kishin away.
That binding kept
him trapped in the city.
There is nothing he
desired more than this...
To come here
to this battlefield.
And Brew made that possible...
by mobilizing all of Death City!
All right then...
let's see what this baby can do!
Mosquito...
launch a counterattack.
Understood, my lady.
Launching counterattack.
That one can move too?!
Fools!
What...?!
This is insanity!
This can't be happening.
This is so cool!
Let's dance!
Well, here goes nothin'!
Why can't I swat that damn bug?!
Careful, Dad...!
Don't kill us!
Take this, bug!
And this!!
Nice try, Reaper!
Hot hot hot hot hot hot hot!
Hot! Hot!
Really, really hot!
Dad, what're you doing?!
Eye Poke!!
Special Attack...
Coffee Table Flip!!
Impossible!
Fools!
Now it's my turn.
So this is what a
Death Scythe can do...?
That's incredible!
Target located...
Mapping it now.
The upper level of the
castle near the middle...
That's where the Kishin is.
Thank you, Azusa.
Good job...
Same to you students...
you've performed well today.
Hold on tightly!
It's not over yet!
Die, Reaper!!
Playtime's over!
What now?!
No!
Hm.
He swallowed the Kishin whole!
♪ closing song ♪
Dad ate the Kishin!
Hey, hey...!
Doesn't that mean
it's all over...?
Is this the end of the show?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
The audience is never gonna
buy that kind of ending!
But the Kishin's all eaten!
What else is left to do?
Well...
...it's a bit...
complicated...
So it's not over?
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Lord Death Wields
a Death Scythe...
Just One Step
from Utter Darkness?
Oh goodie!
There's still more to come!