[Maka] A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
♪ opening song ♪
[Patty]
Hot!
[Liz] What are we doing
in this wasteland...?
It's hot and sandy and horrible!
[Patty]
So hot!
[Kid]
Quit complaining.
We're here on Dad's orders...
You guys have heard of the
"Runaway Express," right...?
The high-speed train that runs
through the desert without
following any tracks?
[Patty]
Hot!
Oh yeah, the one that's run
continuously for over
a hundred years now?
[Kid]
That's right.
A century's a long time to
run without maintenance.
How does it work?
[Kid] Apparently it's
powered by a Magic Tool.
What's that?
[Kid] A device that could cause
wide-spread destruction
if used by the wrong people.
It seems that Arachnophobia
would like to get their
hands on this one...
[Patty]
So hot!
It's... so... freakin
hot out here!!!
[Kid]
That's why we're here.
We must reach
the tool before they do.
[Maka] The Red Hot
Runaway Express!
o~A Magic Tool Left Behind
by the Grand Wizard?o~
Hot!
[Liz] Kid,
I thought that as a
Grim Reaper you were
immune to sunburn...
What's the point of wearing
that silly outfit in this heat?
It sets the mood...
Besides, it keeps the lines in
my hair partially hidden...
No matter how
many times I dye it,
those damn lines
keep coming back...
Quite annoying.
[Patty]
...so hot...
[Kid]
Here we are.
[Liz] A station in the
middle of the desert?
[Kid] Let's get going...
The train'll arrive
any minute now.
[Liz] You sound pretty
excited about that.
[Patty]
How come?
That train has been operating
on schedule for
the last hundred years.
Never a second late
or a second early.
How could I not be excited
about seeing such a perfectly
executed mode of transportation?
[Liz]
Right. How silly of me.
[Kid]
Someone's already there...
It looks like a child.
[Kid] Well, the train
is famous, I guess.
[Kid] Hello there...
Sure is hot today, isn't it?
[Liz]
Hello!
[Patty]
Hello...
Hey, midget,
where are your manners?!
Aren't you gonna answer us...?!
When someone says 'hello',
you answer, okay?!
Calm down.
Hey! Who do you think you are,
clicking your tongue
at us like that, huh...?!
That's it! I'm gonna kill you!
[Liz] Oh, wow! Look at
all the sand, Patty...!
Why don't we sit here
and play for awhile?
[Patty] Yeah! I'm gonna
build a sandcastle!
[Kid]
According to the schedule,
the train should
be arriving soon.
Is that why you're here...?
The Runaway Express?
Chi-chi-chi...
All done!
Wow...! Looks great, Patty!
I don't know what it is,
but there's something not
quite right about
that kid up there.
I still don't see anything!
At this rate, it's going to
miss its scheduled arrival.
So, its perfect punctuality
was nothing more
than a rumor...
How disappointing.
[Patty]
Aww... it fell down.
[Kid gasps]
[train whistle blows]
[metal clanging and
rolling on tracks]
[Liz cries out]
[Patty]
Awesome!
[Fisher King laughs]
[Fisher King] The Grim Reaper
sent his minions, I see!
Well, you're too late...
This big fish is
mine for the taking!
The Magic Tool belongs
to Arachne...Fisher!
That's the agent Arachne
sent to get the tool.
Chi-chi-chi...
[Kid]
What?
A witch's soul...?
So that kid wasn't
a tourist after all...?
Though I suppose witches
can be tourists too...
Uh-oh!
[Kid]
That settles it...
Tourists don't leave bombs.
Man, that train can really move!
Oh wow... it looks
like an earthworm!
You can admire it later.
Right now I need
you to transform.
--Yeah, got it!
--Got it!
[Kid]
Let's go...!
Go...! Go...! Go!
[Kid]
There it is.
[Fisher King laughs]
I'm the first one aboard...!
The Magic Tool
is mine for the taking!
Impossible...!
He's already caught up?
Fishing Rod Launcher!
[Patty]
Watch out, Kid...
Incoming missile, ten o'clock.
[impact blast]
[Fisher King]
Do you like my fishing rod...?
Do you like my missiles?
How does that feel?
[Fisher King laughs
hysterically]
[Fisher King shocked]
What happened?
[Mizune]
Chi-chi-chi.
I can use this to my advantage.
The smoke will
hide my approach.
[Patty] Kid, the train's
about to turn right.
Not good!
What now...?
Dodging attacks from both
the side and above while trying
to board a runaway train
that moves at 500 kilometers
an hour is not easy.
Patty, can I leave this to you?
[Patty]
Yeah!
I'll finish 'im as soon
as he shows his ugly face!
He's all yours!
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
Gotcha...! Die, fisher guy!
[Kid] Three Hundred
Sixty Degree...
...Kick-Flip!
[Patty cries out]
Nice one.
What are you doing, Kid?
This isn't the time to be
showing off your
skateboard skills!
Don't you know anything...?!
That was an incredible hill
we ran over back there...
Given the situation it
would've been wrong not to
have done a trick or two on it.
[Liz]
What?!
Look, we've got another
one coming up...!
Patty, it's a no-hander!
[Patty cries out]
Thirty... six hundred!
[Patty]
I'm getting dizzy!
[Fisher King] What are
they doing up there?
[Kid] Good...
Now transform, Patty.
[Patty weakly]
Yeah...
[incoming missle hiss]
[explosions]
[Mizune]
Chi-chi-chi!
I'm a sitting duck up here...
There's no sign of the guy...
He must've gone up to the front.
[Fisher King laughs]
All I have to
do is pull this lever,
and it's "bye-bye" to anyone
in the cars behind me!
[Fisher King laughs]
All right, where'd
the guy run off to?
Got 'im!
[Fisher King] You move
fast, skateboard kid.
But that won't keep you
from blowing up along
with this half of the train!
Damn it...!
He's going to uncouple the cars!
[Fisher King laughs]
That was close!
I forgot that I had to
watch for attacks
from the air, too.
But no one catches
the Fisher King!
Avoiding that attack landed
me on the wrong
side of the train!
Fisher!
This guy's a special
kind of stupid.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Seriously!
[Fisher King]
Damn!
And...Fisher!
Well... see ya around!
Liz, Patty!
[Liz]
Connect!
[Patty]
[Fisher King]
What the--?
[Liz and Patty cry out]
We're flying!
How cool!
[Fisher King]
Damn it!
I can taste victory...!
No one's getting into
the engine room ahead of me!
[Liz]
Where's he going?
[Kid]
Liz, Patty.
[Fisher King]
Fishing Rod Launcher!
Die, die, die, die, die,
die, die, die, die, die!
Geez. This guy is stupid,
ugly, and a bad shooter!
[Fisher King]
Die, die, die, die, die!
Hey!
[Fisher King]
Damn...
That's it!
That's the train's power source!
The Magic Tool...
Known as The Eternal Spring.
I've got it!
You're too late!
[Kid bellows]
[Fisher King]
You can't have it...
It belongs to
the witch Arachne.
[Kid] This is what we
came here for...
After it's gone, the Runaway
Express will sleep.
This is an evil tool...
Just holding it disgusts me.
[Fisher King laughs]
I see you're a typical
ignorant student of
the academy...
That tool was created
by the Grand Wizard Eibon...
It's a work of genius.
What? Eibon...?
If he made this,
he's an evil piece of trash.
[Fisher King] Would you say
that of Lord Death as well?
What does my father
have to do with this?!
[Fisher King]
Oh, how cute...
So you're the Grim
Reaper's son, are you?
Then let me show
you something.
Open the box that held
the Eternal Spring
and look inside.
That box there...?
What's in it that I need to see?
[Fisher King] Eibon's tool
isn't just the spring alone...
It also includes the box
you see there with
the keyhole in it...
That's where you need to look.
Go on...! Open it...!
Open it...!
You know you want to...
Read what's written on
the plate inside the box!
It says... Eibon... and then...
Below that it says... it says...
"Death"...
There's no mistaking it...
That's Dad's handwriting.
Why would Dad's signature
be on something evil like this?
[Liz]
What's wrong Kid?
[Fisher King]
Yes... What's wrong?
Could it be you find
what's written there
a tad disturbing...?
Whose signature is it you
see there on that evil tool?
What's the meaning of this...?
Tell me what's going on here!
[Fisher King]
Eibon is...
What was that?
[Mizune]
Chi.
What's he doing here?
It's Sid.
[Sid] I'll take care
of the others
with a collection squad
from the African branch.
You guys go get some rest.
This soul belongs to you, Kid...
Go ahead and take it.
[Desert soldier 1]
Get it! Shoot it down!
[Mizune]
Chi chi chi.
[Desert soldier 2] Sid, there
was a witch here, too...
She escaped.
Our objective was
the Eternal Spring...
Let the witch go.
[Desert soldier 2]
Okay, kids...
You head on to the
camp for some rest...
There'll be cold drinks
waiting for you.
Yea...! Thank you, mister!
Awesome... Thanks.
Yeah... thanks.
[Liz]
Finally! Outta this heat!
Objective has been completed...
The DWMA has
another Magic Tool.
[Kid]
Nothing there.
I'm not finding anything
even remotely useful in the
level one reference books.
Would you say that
of Lord Death as well?
[Kid thinks]
Who exactly is Eibon?
Yes, may I help you...?
Is there a specific
book you need?
Actually, I'd like to see any
materials that you have
in the Level Four
Block regarding
the person known as Eibon.
Let me see your student ID.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
Students with up to
two stars can check out
books from the second level...
Faculty can view all
Level Three materials.
Only Death Scythes and
select high-ranking meisters
may access Level Four.
You are only a
one-star meister...
As such, you may only check
out books from the first level.
Take a look at
the back of my card.
Okay.
Please excuse me.
I didn't realize you
were a member of
Lord Death's family.
I'll find the books you
asked for immediately, sir.
Please wait here a moment.
[Kid]
Thank you.
[Kid thinks] I'm still only
a one-star meister...
I'd hoped to have been much
further along than that by now.
If I ask Dad straight out,
he'll brush me off like
he did when I asked
about the Kishin.
I have to find out myself.
[Kid]
Have you found it?
Yes... One book does
match your request...
It contains information
about Eibon.
Great. Can you please direct me
to the shelf that
it's on...It's urgent.
Unfortunately, it seems that the
book was lent out two months ago
and has not yet been returned.
[Kid] Do you know
who borrowed it...?
If necessary, I'll track down
whoever it is myself
and ask that they return it.
Again, I'm deeply sorry, sir...
Due to insufficient records...
I do not know who was the
last person to check it out.
The signature line
has no name on it...
There's only the letter M...
Nothing more, I'm afraid.
I'm very sorry.
Please forgive my
negligence in this.
[Kid thinks]
Who besides me would
have an interest in
a book like that?
It was taken out of the
library two months ago.
On the first of April.
The day the Kishin revived?
M...
M?!
Was it Medusa?
[closing song]
[Patty]
Choo choo!
[Liz]
Aww, I'm sunburned!
Do you know what that
does to my beautiful skin?!
Choo choo!
[Patty] Excalibur's back in
the next episode!
Choo choo!
[Liz] No, Patty, next time
it's about the party.
Choo choo!
[Patty]
Parties are fun!
Honk honk meow!
[Liz] That's not what
a train sounds like.
Choo choo!
[Patty] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Drying Happiness...
Whose Tears Sparkle
in the Moonlight?
Choo choo!
[Liz] What kind
of preview is this?
Choo choo!