[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[heels clicking on the floor]
[Eruka]
I brought it...
You'll remove one of
the snakes from inside me now,
like you said you would, right?
[Medusa]
Of course.
You've done well Eruka...
good work.
[Medusa]
Finally.
Free... How is your Magic Eye?
Ah...In perfect shape now...
I should be able to control
an independent cube easily.
[Medusa]
With that eye,
the Grandwitch was an
expert in spatial magic...
Now that the Magic eye
belongs to you,
you'll be needed tonight...
Eruka and I will be lending
you support with
computation spells...
We're counting on you.
Yeah... Just leave it to me.
Now... the time has come.
I've been waiting
for this night.
[explosions of fireworks]
♪ opening song ♪
It'll start without
us if you don't hurry.
You're the one who
took forever with all
the primping you had to do.
Hey, Soul...!
I'm gonna eat a bunch
of food until I puke!
[Tsubaki thinks]
How... gentlemanly.
[Patty]
Over here guys!
Hey, take a look
at these guys...
They're dressed up
all fancy-pants.
[Maka]
What's wrong, Kid...?
You don't seem very excited.
Oh... I'm sorry.
I'm so hungry!
How... gentlemanly.
Anyway, everybody,
thank you so much for coming...
Tonight we celebrate
the founding of the DWMA!
[Maka] The Eve
Party Nightmare...
And So the Curtain Rises?
[crowd talking]
[Kid]
Please, come inside...
My father will be
giving his greeting shortly.
Hungry.
[Kid thinks] Can what Father
told me actually be true?
Something like
that exists here?
Yo...! Hey...! Hiya...!
Thanks for coming...!
Great to see you!
[Man]
It's Lord Death!
[Woman]
Wow...! Lord Death!
[Death]
Okay, well...
...that's about
all I have to say...
Have a great time tonight!
[Soul thinks]
That was kind of short.
[Kid thinks] Father isn't
taking this seriously.
All...If I may speak as well...
Thank you for taking
the time to come here...
Tonight at this gala,
we celebrate something
dear to all of our hearts...
the founding of our academy.
If you will kindly indulge me...
I, Death the Kid...
...would like to say a few
[Soul thinks]
Man, he's a real pro.
We all know the
mission of this school...
to maintain peace
in this world...
In all my glory...!
The one and only,
amazing Black Star yeah!
...Of course,
this is all thanks to--
Hear Me, people...!
It's Me with a capital 'm'.
I'm the only one big
enough to capitalize 'Me.'
Anyway... as I was saying...
Disgusted Dash!
[Black Star] What do you
think you're doing...?!
You can't interrupt
my big speech!
[Kid] You're the one
who interrupted,
you hopeless idiot...!
I wanted my speech to
be precise and exact!
It's ruined...
I want to die!
That jerk...!
Whose party does he
think this is, anyway?
You do realize it's
not yours, don't you?
[Death] Well, is this a
party or isn't it...?
There's a band and lots
of food, so eat, sing, dance,
do the hokey-pokey.
Whatever you're in the mood for!
[All]
Yeah!
[Tsubaki thinks]
There he goes...
Kick your legs up to
a ninety degree angle...!
They should match perfectly.
'Kay!
How embarrassing.
[Maka laughs]
This kind of fancy party
really isn't my scene.
[Maka]
Soul.
Hey, Maka. What's up?
The food's great tonight.
Don't you want to eat something?
I don't feel like standing
in line for some fancy food...
...besides, eating while you're
standing up is awkward.
You're missing out, Soul.
This stuff is delicious.
Fine, then gimme some of yours.
No.
Food hog.
How's Soul?
Is he still having that
strange dream
with the demon in it...?
He seemed to be
quite troubled by it.
[Maka]
Uh... Soul...
It seems like something's
been eating at you lately.
Huh...? What makes you say that?
I'm sorry... I thought he
would've told you about it.
He told me.
You can talk to me about
these things, you know.
[Soul]
Sure, but nothing's wrong.
Uh... what is it?
[Maka thinks] I probably
shouldn't pry too much into it.
So... that's how it is...
You think I'm an unreliable
partner, don't you?
You said it, not me.
Whatever! Like you
have any room to talk!
You're not so great!
Yea...! Let's dance!
Huh...? Forget about it.
I don't wanna.
Oh, come on...
You know you're
a good dancer, Soul...
I'll let you lead...
Besides, dancing is good
for matching soul
wavelengths, so quit arguing.
[Death Scythe]
Hold it right there!
Come dance with your papa.
No way.
[Soul]
Talk about perfect timing.
All children need to bond
with their parents, Maka...
You should go dance with him.
I don't feel like bonding.
Soul is exactly right!
--Let's dance, Maka!
--Enough already. You win.
I'm coming! Soul,
guard my food, will you?
She wants me
to guard her food...
...yet she refused
to let me have any.
Huh?
She can't stand raw fish...
What is she doing getting
salmon from the buffet?
Fickle woman.
Oh... it's for me.
That was dumb...
It's not like I need
any help from her.
Oh well... It does look good.
[Eruka]
Medusa...
We've entered Death City...
What do you
want us to do now?
Wait at the designated spot
for the signal from us.
One more thing...
Have we obtained the
assistance we need?
[Eruka telepathically] It's all
set... Crona, or should I say,
Ragnarok... will be
leading them here soon.
All right... Good work, Eruka.
Well hello there, Dr. Medusa...
You're having fun, I hope?
Oh... Hello, Professor Stein.
My...! You're always
sneaking up on me!
[Medusa thinks]
This guy again?
You should go ahead and
drink that before I do. Cheers.
Uh... Are you all right,
Professor Stein?
Oh...! Sorry,
I'm a bit drunk...!
I must have had
too much champagne!
[Medusa thinks] Is he faking
it...? I can't read him.
What d'ya say...?
Let's go dancing!
[Stein] Come on,
don't be a party pooper!
We're all dressed up
and everything!
[Medusa thinks]
Someone help.
[Death Scythe] Know what I'm
thinking about, Maka?
The last time we danced...
It was the day of your
kindergarten graduation...
You danced on my feet...
And then afterwards I
danced with your mama...
What a great day!
[Maka] It wasn't Mama you
were dancing with.
It was actually Sara's mother.
[Death Scythe thinks] Oh,
crap...! Was it really...?
Oh, boy did
I screw that one up...
Leave it to Maka to
remember that far back.
Anyway... I'm
dancing with you now,
and that's what
counts, isn't it...?
Tonight will be a great memory!
I promise you, Maka...
I'm going to be a better Papa.
No way.
[Medusa thinks]
What am I doing...?
I have to get off
this dance floor...
I can't let Eruka and the
others see me like this.
[Stein]
Dr. Medusa?
Professor Sid has been
gone for quite a while now...
Do you know anything about that?
[Medusa] Oh...?
I'm afraid I don't know
anything that could help you...
I do hope he's
all right, though.
You're sure you don't know...?
He went to investigate a
laboratory somewhere.
Now let me think here...
Who did that laboratory
belong to, again...?
Oh, that's right!
It was your laboratory.
I have no idea what you're
talking about, Professor!
[Stein] I'm curious
to know why a witch
like you would risk
coming to the DWMA.
You really are
quite drunk, aren't you...?
Perhaps I should bring
you a glass of water.
I can do without
the water, thank you...
I wasn't really drunk.
I take it the Kishin is
what you're interested in.
I find it hard to imagine you
snuck into the academy just to
observe what goes on with all
of our weapons and meisters.
More likely--
you know about it,
don't you Witch Medusa...?
About the Kishin sleeping
beneath the DWMA.
[Medusa]
You hopeless fool...
If it weren't for Lord
Death being here...
...you'd be dead now.
Shall we cut to the chase...?
No need to hold back...
I found you out.
You can drop the charade.
All right then...
You're correct, my goal
is to revive the Kishin.
And for that you
needed black blood...
But why? What does it do?
[Medusa] The Kishin's power
surpasses human understanding...
It is evolution itself.
Lord Death and
his little academy
have monitored and protected
the world by acting
as a check against power.
The DWMA seeks only
to maintain the status quo...
That's its mission.
But still...
time continues to march forward.
It's only natural for the
rest of the world to progress
with it, don't you agree...?
That's how nature works.
And yet, Professor Stein,
this academy has made a
point to keep
that from happening...
Do you really want to
live in a world of stasis,
where nothing changes?
You're a scientist like me.
Surely you must understand.
So... why don't you join me?
[Sid]
Stein!
Hurry...! Everyone get
out of here immediately!
Professor Sid?!
[Stein]
Are you okay?
Yeah... but I'm not sure how...
We ran into an ambush.
I dove underground
right before the blast...
...but I barely got away.
[explosions]
[Sid]
No...
What we need to do now
is get everyone outta here.
It's a trap...!
This is the day they've
been waiting for.
When Lord Death leaves
his mirror and
all of the students
and teachers are in one place.
Medusa!
[Medusa thinks] Free...!
The barrier!
Now...! Trap them all inside!
Right. I'm on it...
Now, Soul Protect... release!
[Maka thinks]
What is that?
[Free]
Wolf Wolves...
Wolf Wolves.
This will prevent
any interference...
Anyone who gets trapped inside
this magic box will
be unable to escape.
[Medusa]
Eruka, hurry...!
We need to get the
box's position set.
Ribbit, ribbit.
[Medusa]
Computation spell...
Magic Calculation!
What... what is this?
It's starting now... Naigus...
...you ready?
We need soul resonance.
[Naigus]
Yeah.
We have to get these guys out.
[Free] Appearance
position confirmed...
Spatial Magic:...
Independent Cube! Now!
What's going on?
The room is--!
Key create!
This is gonna be close...
[Free]
Set!
What's happening out there?
What's going on?
I'm sensing something.
I can feel a spatial warping...
That's it...!
They're locking us in!
Here we go...! Forced Burial!
Coffins? What are these for?
[Free]
Lock!
[Maka cries out]
No, Sid.
We're counting on you...
to protect the DWMA.
We've got one hour, Medusa...
It won't hold longer than that.
In that case...
...let's get gone before
Death shows up.
We don't have a single
second to waste...
Where's Crona?
[Ragnarok cries out]
I brought them
just like you said...
The Mizune family.
[Eruka]
Mizunes!
[Eruka thinks] The only
reason they came to help
was because I lied and
said that the academy
killed the oldest
Mizune sister...
I had to do it...
but I'm so sorry, Mizunes.
[Medusa]
That's it, Mizunes...
I'll leave the rest in
your mousy little hands...
Bring Death City crashing
down around their heads.
Eruka... You've got
the attaché case?
Right here!
We're headed underground.
[Medusa thinks]
I will revive the Kishin.
[Soul] The meisters
landed on their feet,
and the weapons didn't...
I guess we really are different.
I'm sensing some
witch souls up there...
One... two... eight of them...!
And the Demon Sword, also!
What was that?
What are they doing up there?
[Stein]
Listen up kids...
We've got an
emergency on our hands.
Below the DWMA...
...sleeps a Kishin...
...the source of
all madness in the world.
You should know,
our school nurse
Medusa is a witch...
She snuck into the
academy to revive the Kishin.
We must stop this at all costs.
Doctor Medusa is actually
a witch, professor...?
That's crazy.
And this Kishin, too...?
How's something like
that beneath the school?
[Kid]
It's true.
My father explained
everything to me...
In order to keep
the Kishin sleeping,
safe and sound...
...my father cannot ever
leave the academy.
Huh...? So there's a reason
Lord Death never
goes anywhere...?
I always thought he just
wasn't much of
a people person...
Let's get moving...
We can't let Sid's quick
thinking go to waste.
All of you follow me...
I'll take us to the entrance
that leads underground.
[Woman]
It didn't budge.
[Death] Oh my... We're in
a real pickle here...
...yep... Quite a predicament.
[Kilik]
Lord Death!
You need to get
out of here, sir...
Can you escape through this?
[Death]
A mirror?
Unfortunately,
that's a no-can-do.
You see, there wouldn't
be anywhere to go...
This space is cut off
from all other worlds.
At best a high-octane spell
like this will only hold up
for an hour or so.
There isn't a whole lot
we can do until then.
Oh. I understand.
Sorry about that, kid.
Damn!
We've been acting
so complacent...
We're just too used to peace.
[Death] Hey, now...
there's nothing wrong
with being used to peace.
I think we should
get more used to it...
Because that would mean
the world is a peaceful place.
So we're gonna sit here,
preserving the peace.
Because that's what this
academy was built for.
As for the rest of it...
...it's all up to them now.
[Stein]
This is the entrance we need.
Our enemy is powerful.
If you aren't prepared
for what lies ahead...
...then you may die.
If you want to turn around...
better do it now.
Are you ready to fight
against fear itself...?
Will you cross
beyond that door...?
Let your souls make
the decision for you.
We're coming!
[Stein]
Good.
♪ closing song ♪
[Soul] Let's fight.
Let's do this.
I'm ready. Let's get going!
[Maka] Whoa, Soul...
You're too worked up...
Calm down a little, okay?
[Soul] What are
you talking about?
Why shouldn't I be
pumped right now...
[Maka] In situations like this,
you need to keep your cool...
Let's try a little exercise...
Repeat after me...
"I will be cool."
[Soul] Sounds kinda dumb to me,
but fine... I will be cool...
I will be cool...
Okay, can we fight now?
[Maka]
Oh, never mind!
[Soul] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Underground
Battle Commences...
Break Through
Medusa's Vector Arrow?~
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!