A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
With the Battle for Brew
seemingly complete,
each side moved on to the
next step of their plan.
Some students, however,
cannot forget their failure.
Meanwhile, I began investigating
my dad's intentions for
collecting Eibon's dangerous
works. I wanted the truth.
But the information I
obtained only deepened
my suspicions of the
academy's recent activities.
I made it...
Death City My new workplace.
Well, let's get started.
♪ opening song ♪
Hello, hello... I'm so
glad to see you're here.
It's always good to see
a representative from
our technology division.
Do you prefer your full name,
Joe Butataki... Or do
you still go by JB?
Everything okay?
Yeah. Everything's fine...
Let's talk about why
you called me here.
Your summons seemed urgent.
Should I assume that the
project's already begun?
Aren't you getting a bit
ahead of yourself...?
I haven't even told you what
you're doing here yet.
Yes, I'm sorry but ...
why else would you
have called me,
if not for that?
Of course that's why, but
can't you let me say it?
You're kinda stealing
my thunder here...
Besides, there are
some new developments
you should know about...
We lost our most recent
battle with Arachnophobia...
and Brew is now in their hands.
That makes your presence
here all the more important.
It sounds like the academy's
at a serious disadvantage now.
Indeed we are... And I'm
not sure there's much
of anything I can do about it.
So, what happens to the plan
now that the enemy has Brew?
Well, fortunately,
we've managed to acquire a
number of Eibon's
other Magic Tools.
And that's where
you come in...!
What do you say:
Given the circumstances,
can you help keep
our plan on track?
The plan was my idea.
I'd hate to see it ruined...
I'll give it a try.
I knew I could count on you!
However, I have one
condition before I start.
And that condition would be...?
The coffee...
Coffee?
This is a disgrace!
Instant coffee?!
I won't work here until this
--Now, now, let's
keep calm here.
--shameful practice has
been stopped...!
--There's no need to
get so excited.
--You must get rid of this
disgusting powder,
--Perhaps you've had a bit
too much caffeine today.
--and replace it
with whole beans!
And they must come
from Uncle Bob's!
Only the finest
quality will do!
This point is non-negotiable!
I also require that you
stock my preferred
brand of coffee creamer!
Finally, the filters must
be made of sturdy paper
so no grounds will
pollute the coffee!
Coffee beans?
Yes, coffee beans!
Asura's Temptation: The Big
Man's Uncontrollable Irritation?
You serious?
First Kid disappears,
now Black Star's
taken off, too?
What's gotten into
everyone around here?
That's not all. Tsubaki's gone
too... I wonder what's going on.
Couldn't tell ya.
Something's been
bothering Black Star.
He hasn't been himself lately...
He seems so dispirited.
Why do I keep losing?
I'm supposed to be the one
who'll surpass God...
So why? Why?!
Why do you desire
such great power?
Black Star didn't show up
to class. I wonder where he is.
Tsubaki.
Oh, hi Naigus.
Do you have a sec?
What's a consultant from
the tech division...
...doing at the academy?
News travels fast around
here, doesn't it?
I only just got in and already
the questions have started.
So who's that make you?
The welcome wagon?
Death the Kid, actually...
I was named after my father.
I see... So your Lord Death's
little son, are you?
What brings you to
the academy...?
You've come a long way.
What part do you have to
play in my dad's plans?
Construction.
The plumbing here at
the academy is old.
It's in pretty bad shape...
That's why I'm here.
Not even a good lie. You'll
have to do better than that.
You wouldn't have come all
this way for plumbing.
Well... uh...
Of course that isn't
the only reason!
The boiler needs some
work done on it too.
Now that's a job for the
tech division... huh?
It might be if the
academy had a boiler.
In the past few months,
the academy's bent
all its efforts on
collecting Magic Tools.
And then, out of nowhere,
a technology expert just
happens to show up...
So you'll excuse me if
I think there's something
more to this than our pipes.
If these Magic Tools are as
rusty as my poker face,
I'm going to have a lot more
work than I bargained for.
Come back...!
I'm not done talking.
Here's some free advice.
Huh?
Let it go... I'm here
to do some work.
That's all you need to know.
So, tell me...
How's Uncle Bob doing?
Uncle Bob?
The man who runs the coffee
shop not far from here.
Uncle Bob's Rumba Coffee...!
"So delicious it'll make you
dance!" Come on, everybody!
Do the Rumba! Shake
your hips and do the
--Uncle Bob's coffee
rumba with me!
--I don't know what
you're talking about.
--Uncle Bob's coffee
rumba with me!
You don't know Uncle Bob?
That's a crying shame, kid.
Hey!
Here it is.
Lord Death's vault...
It's time to get started.
It's over, kid.
It isn't over yet.
Not until I've beaten you.
Black Star.
You don't understand
the Enchanted Sword.
You won't ever be able to
harness its full power...
You aren't strong enough.
What do you know?!
I'm Black Star.
I can do anything!
No. No, you can't.
It's all over... Just give up.
You have lost.
I've been looking
all over for you.
I'm here.
It's the last place
I checked, of course.
What're you doing here?
Thinking about how
I'm going surpass God.
Why am I not surprised?
Should you be skipping class?
I skipped class to see
where you were...
I didn't expect to end up on
the roof, but here we are.
Yeah... here we are.
I ran into Naigus...
She told me not to use
the Enchanted Sword
mode anymore.
What?
She said it's been putting
too much strain on your body.
Yeah right.
What a joke...
Nothing could make me
give up on mastering
the Enchanted Sword.
I understand.
How could you give up...?
You haven't surpassed God yet.
No... not yet.
What is it?
Oh, hey, Kid. You're back.
And where did you run off to?
Sorry. I was busy...
I had some things to look into.
What kinda things?
What could be so important
that you had to look
into it without telling
us where you were going?
I'll explain it later,
after class is over...
It's a long story...
For now there's something
else I need you
to help me with.
What?
Where have you been, Kid?
Is everything okay?
Of course.
Everything's just fine.
I can't afford to let any
of the other students know
what I'm up to. It's
too soon for that...
For now, this
investigation's a solo job.
It's Black Star.
You finally showed up...
Do you know what time it is?
I came for you, Kid...
Step outside for a second.
What's this about...?
Are you having some sort
of a problem here?
I wanted to show you something.
What are you doing?!
Yahoo!!
Not again?!
Look what you did, you idiot!
The DWMA building was
perfectly symmetrical,
and now you've destroyed it!
How could you?!
Come on down here, Kid.
Let's fight about it.
What?
So, how's Crona doing?
He's been acting
strange lately...
Something seems to
be bothering him.
Why do you say that...?
Has he asked any questions
recently that seem out of
the ordinary for him?
Well... Now that you mention
it, he did ask about Stein's
condition after the
battle on Lost Island.
Oh? That is unexpected...
Why would a child like
Crona be concerned
about Professor Stein?
I don't get it.
He seemed really shaken up.
How unfortunate.
Poor Crona...I don't think he'll
be of use to me much longer.
What's going on?
Why are you guys fighting?
I don't see what's
so surprising...
Black Star gets into
fights all the time.
Yeah, but still...
So, Black Star...
Huh?
Taking on Kid this time, are we?
The ref's here.
We can get started now.
Hold on, both of you...!
What's the point of this stupid
duel in the first place!...?
This is ridiculous!
What Tsubaki?
I'm sorry, but... This is
something Black Star
feels he has to do, so
please don't interfere.
You brought this on
yourself, Black Star...
You knew damn well
how I'd react if
the academy's symmetry
was destroyed!
Reaper Combat Art: Mortal Sin
Stance. There's no helping it.
I have to beat you to
a pulp very quickly
then immediately see to
the necessary repairs.
Let's go.
You going to take your
hands out of your pockets?
Are you trying to win this
thing without using your hands?
Maybe I am.
Damn.
That's fast.
No time to block!
Here comes his soul wavelength.
It's all over.
What was that?
Black Star.
Do you remember the
first time we met...?
We fought in this
exact same place...
Since then, you've
improved your fighting
technique significantly.
You've got more style.
But I have to say...
You've gotten a bit weak.
He's lost confidence in himself.
That's why his Soul Force
attack didn't work.
His wavelength is
paralyzed by doubt.
Is that even possible?!
I've seen it happen before...
It doesn't take much to
change a soul wavelength.
Doubting yourself will
do it every time.
I've known Black Star for a long
time... Since he was an infant.
He has great talent.
His soul is strong.
He's willing to work hard.
Against a single opponent
or many, it doesn't matter...
He'll beat them
all, one by one.
That's what he does. That's who
he is: someone who wins.
But lately he's begun to lose
fights, one after the other.
His battle with the samurai
Mifune was the most damaging.
It was a total defeat.
If you think back, you'll
see that was about the
time when his attitude
started to change.
He can't handle his
recent losses...
He wasn't built to lose.
That's why he's been so angry?
It goes back even
further, I think.
His difficulties with the
Enchanted Sword have
been a blow to his
self-confidence.
I can't blame him...
Someone with a weaker
soul would have given
up a long time ago.
But that little idiot
doesn't even know
the meaning of giving up.
You're quiet... Do you want to
tell me what's on your mind?
What's on my mind...? Just that
I'm surrounded by morons!
Why's he have to keep
pushing himself so hard...?
I'm sure he'll get the
hang of it sooner
or later if he'll just wait.
A long time ago, when I was
alive, I was a handsome man.
Huh?
We adults are often
stuck in the past...
...and children can only
think about the future.
But Black Star lives
in the present...
He can't wait for the future...
He has to find his path now.
Find my path? It's not about
finding... It's about winning.
Stop spouting your useless
philosophies... Stupid zombie.
Sid.
I see it. Those eyes...
That wavelength.
White Star.
Is he following
his father's path?
Black Star! Let's forget
about the broken cone...
Just walk away!
I can't walk away now!
And I'll kill you before
I let you give up either!
What happened, Black Star...?
Who are you?
Your dream. I thought you
wanted to surpass God.
Um...
There's no need to apologize...
This isn't the last time
it's going to happen.
It's who he is.
I know.
The important thing is
what happens next...
Can he really keep
living like this?
He's doing better now.
I think he'll be all right...
He's just got a few things
left to learn, that's all.
Yeah... I hope you're right.
What are you waiting for...?
This was your idea.
Yeah, yeah, I know, I know...
What's the big deal...?
Just go in there and ask how
he's doing or something.
Or do you not care
about him at all?
How could you even say
that...! He's our teammate.
Of course I care about him!
Then why are you still
standing out here in the hall?
Get in there!
No...! Wait!
I haven't thought of
something appropriate
to say yet...!
No, please, Soul!
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred fifty six...
four hundred fifty seven...
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred fifty eight...
four hundred fifty nine...
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred sixty...
four hundred sixty one...
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred sixty-two...
four hundred sixty-three...
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred sixty-four...
four hundred sixty-five...
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred sixty-six...
four hundred sixty-seven...
Thirty-three thousand,
four hundred sixty-eight...
I found him.
Lady Arachne. I have
excellent news to report...
At long last,
Eibon's Moral Manipulation
Machine is complete.
That's good news indeed...
The other preparations
have been made as well.
Things are about to get very
interesting for the DWMA.
How could he do this to me?!
How am I supposed to
dance the coffee rumba now?
♪ closing music ♪
On the next episode of Soul
Eater... Crona's Escape...!
Show Me Your Smile,
Please? Yahoo!
On the next episode of Soul
Eater... Crona's Escape...!
Show Me Your
Smile, Please?
I hope it goes okay.
On the next episode of Soul
Eater... Crona's Escape...!
Show Me Your
Smile, Please?
It's even better
the second time!
On the next episode of Soul
Eater... Crona's Escape...!
Show Me Your
Smile, Please?
I won't be there, but have fun!
On the next episode of Soul
Eater... Crona's Escape...!
Show Me Your
Smile, Please?
Watch it...
or I'll take your soul...!
That's how it goes, right?