[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
It's okay, really...
I promise you.
It's not that you don't know
how to deal with people...
It's that no one ever took
the time to deal with you.
What do you say?
Will you let me
be your friend, Crona...
Please say you will.
[Soul] You can't succeed without
the madness, huh...? Hah!
How does it feel to
have been so wrong...?
Maybe you should take
up a different hobby...
The music thing
doesn't really suit you.
[door groans and
shuts with echo]
[Demon]
Oh... He left.
Oh well, that's all right...
The door will
always be unlocked.
But still...
...what his girlie
did back there...
Was it really an
exorcism wavelength?
♪ opening song ♪
The black blood has
been stopped somehow.
The fight between Maka
and the Demon Sword at the
second barrier has ended...
I can feel both of their
souls beginning to relax now.
And Maka...?
Is my darling daughter alright?
She is...
It looks like she was
able to grasp on to the
Demon Sword's
wavelength somehow...
The sword meister's
wavelength is stabilizing.
[Crona] I've never cried this
much before in my life.
How am I supposed
to deal with my tears...?
There're so many of them.
[Soul] Maka, we're
running out of time.
We need to get moving.
But we can't just
leave him like this.
He's a wreck.
Just our luck.
[Ragnarok]
Screw you guys.
Damn you, little girl!
You're tiny!
[Ragnarok]
What the hell did you do?!
Why am I so little now?
[Crona muffled]
Hey, get off me...!
How should I know?!
Let go of her!
[Ragnarok]
You and Crona...?
Friends...?
You gotta be kidding me!
Who'd wanna be friends with
a pathetic thing like him...?
He isn't even any fun.
[Crona]
Quit it... get off!
[Ragnarok]
Wait, I got it!
You wanna keep him around
as a punching bag!
Bullying him is an excellent
way to reduce stress.
That's what you want him for!
Get goin' ya little freak.
[Ragnarok]
Well, too bad.
I'm the only one who
gets to beat up Crona.
[Ragnarok] He's mine!
You can't have him.
Please get offa me...
I said, get off now!
[Ragnarok screams]
[Ragnarok] How could you
punch me, Crona...?
I don't believe it...
Do you know how it
feels to be hit by you?!
No. How could I?
[Ragnarok]
Well, I'll tell you...!
It's like when you
haven't crapped
in three days and
three nights...
and then you get a
toilet-water splash back bonus
when you unload it all.
[Crona] That's gross,
and I don't get the comparison.
[Ragnarok] You think I'm gonna
let you talk to me like that?
You guys go ahead without me...
I can handle things back here.
I can hold him off.
I won't let him through.
Here we go!
--Whatcha got under there, huh?
--Hey pervert, let go of me!
Nice dress, pansy.
Don't try to fight back.
You're pathetic.
Oh...kay...
Sure thing. We'll just
leave it to you.
Get him off! Somebody help me!
Try not to die.
[Maka]
The Seal Shrine...
The Immortal Man's Tricks?
[Maka] I wonder if
the others caught up
with the ones who
had the black blood.
[Soul] Are your
wounds healing okay?
Some black scabs have
stopped the bleeding.
I think they're from the
black blood
that was inside me...
They formed when it disappeared.
That makes sense.
But what made the
black blood go away
in the first place?
Huh... good question.
[Soul] Anyway,
we need to stop them
from injecting the
blood into the Kishin.
Kid and Black Star
are after them...
Let's catch up.
It looks like Kid and
the others went this way.
I hope nothing's
happened to them.
Damn...! Can't he at least leave
something for me to do here...?!
How am I supposed
to stand out now?!
[Tsubaki] Shouting a lot is a
good way to stand out!
Now let's hurry.
Right...!
I'm gonna make Kid eat my dust.
[Kid] This place
is a complete mess.
It hardly even looks
like a building anymore.
[Liz]
Don't get distracted.
You don't need to
focus on the mess...
Think about symmetrical
stuff instead.
Butterfly!
The number eight!
[Liz] What? Are you
having a reaction?
Not that.
I can sense the
Kishin's wavelength.
What is it Kid?
You sure you're okay?
Yeah...
It's just this pressure...
I've never sensed
anything like it before.
[Liz] The Kishin's
up ahead, right...?
And you can feel it...?
What's it like?
[Kid]
What's it like...?
That's not an easy
question to answer.
My father only explained
it to me briefly,
so I don't know very much.
Asura was one of my father's
guardians until
he became a Kishin.
Then my father defeated him
and tore off all his skin.
It sounds like your dad
used to be a pretty scary guy...
Why did he do that?
Because he needed to
make a bag to seal Asura in...
It had to be sturdy...
...strong...to lock up
Asura's soul and madness...
What better than
the man's own skin...?
It made the
perfect prison for a Kishin.
After removing all
of Asura's blood,
my father stuffed his
withered body along with
his ruined soul into the
bag and sealed it up tightly.
So now... Asura's body is
starving for blood.
[Liz] That's why they need to
feed him that black blood stuff?
Probably.
Kid, hey...!
There's a heat source!
Right up ahead!
What?!
Cannon fire...?
But from where?
Magic Eye Cannon!
So this is the immortal...
Damn it...
I was so distracted by
the Kishin that
I didn't notice him.
Aww, nice try.
[Kid] Impervious
to bullets, huh...?
In that case,
fighting him head on
would only be a
waste of my time...
I'll have to find a way to
throw him off balance
and then rush past him
when I get the chance.
I've got the upper hand
when it comes
to mobility, though.
Once I get past him,
he'll never catch up.
You're not getting any further!
[Kid] Swiping at my feet!
He's gonna do whatever
he can to reduce my speed.
Missed me!
All right...
I'll try something else.
Go Soul Resonance...!
Execution Mode!
[Liz]
Resonance stable...
Noise level at one
point eight percent.
Feedback in four seconds.
Three.
[Patty]
Two.
One!
Ready to fire!
[Kid]
Death Cannon!
That should've done something.
What...?
Not even the Death
Cannon'll work on him?
This is not good.
[Kid]
What?!... not good.
I need to back up.
[Kid thinks]
Just as I expected.
He won't come after
me from there.
All he wants is to prevent
me from getting through...
If I try to force
my way past him,
he'll rip me to shreds.
Think harder...
I need to connect
these things...
...straighten them up.
Think harder...
Okay...! Yeah, I have it now.
That pillar and that pillar
used to be the top part
and bottom part of
a single pillar.
And that one over there
went in between the two of them.
Excellent...!
Now it all makes sense.
It connects beautifully,
just beautifully!
[Kid] No... that's not what I
need to be thinking about...
The mess doesn't bother me...
Okay... it does
bother me a little...
[Liz]
It's okay, Kid.
Just try to stay focused.
[Kid]
Yeah...
If it's some kind of puzzle
game you're playing,
I'll join you.
I love a good puzzle.
How dare you mock me!
[Kid] Damn it...
Where the hell are
the rest of the pieces
of that broken statue?
And what's up
with that thing...?
It looks like a bad dream you'd
have after eating
too late at night.
Shut up idiot!
This is no time
for art criticism.
Get it together...
That pillar,
could it go over there?
Calm down!
Pillar... statue...
bad dream... top...
bottom, left, right, middle...
This doesn't look good.
I'm impressed Kid managed
to enter an area as messy as
this in the first place,
but he's losing it now...
If he doesn't stop this quickly,
he'll think about it so
much he'll go crazy.
Oh no! He's scratching his
head quicker and quicker...
That's not a good sign.
What now, Sis?
We've gotta do something!
[Kid panicking]
We need to get his mind
off it, but what do we do?
What do we do?!
Yahoo!
Sorry we didn't come sooner!
We caught up to you!
We, I mean, I win!
Too bad, so sad!
No evil Kishin reviving
for you after all!
How does that feel?
Moron...! It's me.
The one we want
is further ahead!
Really...?! That's not
good at all, man...
Wait... in that case,
what're you doing
standing around here then?
Uh-oh, not this guy!
Hey, good one, Black Star...
Now we can get his
focus back on the
werewolf where it belongs.
[Liz]
Kid...! Look!
That man has a ball and chain
on his left foot
but not on his right.
So he does...
How disgusting.
Yeah!
Hey, werewolf...!
I don't let anybody
stand in my way...
Let's get moving, Tsubaki!
Right!
We'll back him.
Let's see you try.
This new runt
could be a problem.
Let's go...! Speed Star!
He's fast...! Where...?
Oh, crap!
Nin!
Why, you...
I've got more.
What's up with this kid?
[Kid thinks]
Hold on...
There's something strange
going on with this guy...
He never even tried
to dodge my attacks...
...but he's doing whatever
he can to avoid Black Star's...
Why is that?
Oh...!
Now I see, he tricked us.
What'd'you say?
What're you doing...?
You want me to tear you up?!
Into eight pieces,
if you don't mind...
Go right ahead,
I won't stop you...
Oh, wait--...
In your current form,
you can't touch me can you?
Finally figured it out, did you?
Hey.
Hey!
Whoa!
[Kid] I take it this is a spell
cast by the Magic Eye...
Yeah... called
Forwarding Vision...
It's a type of Spatial Magic...
It displays a live image
of me while I'm
somewhere else entirely.
How dare you do that
on top of Tadpole Jackson...?!
You'll pay for this! You beast!
I didn't have any other choice.
This was the only way
we could delay them
and keep moving.
What gave me away?
You never tried to avoid any
of the bullets I shot
in your direction.
But... you didn't want any
of Black Star's blade
attacks to hit you...
because they would go
right through you
without resistance,
and we'd realize that you were
nothing more than an image.
I assume the initial cannon
blast came from
behind the projection.
You had to make the image
look like the real deal.
The fact that people generally
prefer to attack immortals
from a distance worked
in your favor, too...
I'm sure you were
counting on that.
All in all, it was a nice trick.
What I wanna know is why
you didn't notice
when you stabbed him!
Hey...! I'm Black Star...
I figured my attacks were
so awesome that my blade
just slid right through
him without me feeling anything.
Really...?!
So then what is
your excuse, Tsubaki?
I just figured he'd
improved a lot,
but I guess I was wrong...huh?
Oh, wow...
Weapons love blindly,
don't they?
Damn...!
They bought themselves a
lot of time with that trick.
Let's hurry, Black Star.
Right!
Time for more action.
Those are good
students you have...
They did well, didn't they...?
They've completed almost
every single assignment that
you've given them today.
But you can sense
it too, can't you...?
It appears the Kishin's
madness has begun to overflow.
Here we go Spirit.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
It won't do you any good now.
Say, tell me something...
How do you raise a good child?
Oh no, Tadpole Jackson!
Aww...!
Are you okay, poor little baby.
Eruka, look at this.
What?
The Kishin must be
through those doors.
We're here.
We need to hurry...
Those little brats'll
catch up to us soon.
[Eruka weakly]
Free...
[Eruka quivers in fear]
[Eruka screams]
My face! I can't
do this anymore!
I'm going home and hibernating!
[Free]
Your face...?
What about your face?
Okay...
calm down now.
[Free]
I can't die. I'm immortal.
What the hell am I doing?!
I-It was...an illusion?
This is the Kishin's madness?
It's not far off...
We're here.
♪ closing song ♪
[Stein] Let's finish this off
with one shot, Spirit.
[Death Scythe] Right... But how
do you plan to cook her goose?
[Stein] I'll start by rubbing it
with some fresh herbs and spices
and roasting it over
low heat for several hours...
Then I'll slice it up
and serve it with a crisp
arugula and spinach salad
and a tasty rice pilaf.
[Death Scythe]
That's not what I meant!
[Stein] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Dead or Alive...!
In the Rift Between
Revival and Dazzlement?
[Death Scythe]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!
[Stein]
And what's worse,
you'll miss out
on Professor Stein's
famous roasted duck.
[Death Scythe] I thought you
were cooking goose?