[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[chains rattling]
[Free]
It's not far off...
We're here.
♪ opening song ♪
[Stein]
We're running out of time.
We need to get Medusa
out of the way and catch up
with the others to stop
the Kishin from reviving.
[Medusa laughs]
[Medusa]
Got you!
Here she comes!
[Medusa laughs]
[Stein thinks] No matter
how she twists and turns,
the snakes underneath her
always keep her balanced...
This woman leaves no openings.
What now?
[Death Scythe]
Medusa hasn't made any
attempts at all to put
an end to this fight.
She's just trying to buy time
by keeping us occupied here.
[Stein thinks]
She's an intuitive witch...
She probably knows that I
won't be able to defeat her
if my head is full
of disturbing thoughts.
Stein, what's
going on with you...?
It seems like you're
losing your edge...
What happened to that ominous
"I'll kill you" vibe you
used to give off?
Quiet, Spirit...
That's exactly what I'm
trying to work on right now.
I'm paying too much attention
to everything that's
going on around me.
I need to get rid
of irrelevant thoughts.
What drives me is curiosity.
I always do my best work when
the subject at
hand intrigues me.
That's what I need to focus on.
The tension is starting
to leave his body.
He may be the DWMA's
greatest meister...
but he's an easy guy to read
if you know what to look for.
[Stein] What is it I want
to do, you ask?
I would think it obvious...
[Death Scythe] It's obvious
you're a sadistic man, Stein.
I want to dissect.
[Maka]
Dead or Alive...!
In the Rift Between
Revival and Dazzlement?
[Medusa chuckles]
Oh, Stein... you're so adorable.
[Death Scythe]
Yeah...
I almost forgot it's my job
to control this head case...
What is the fool up to now?
Please, no more.
I'm begging you.
I'm gonna tear you
into little pieces...
I wonder how
I should do it, though.
Cut up...?
Or gouge out...?
Or simply rip apart?
That's for later, though...
Right now I'll give
you a painless death.
[Young Death Scythe]
Step away!
I think that's enough,
don't you?
Stay out of this, Spirit.
I'm going do
things my way.
So then what...?
You're just going to ignore
all the academy's rules?
Well, what is it
you want to do?
Did you think you could
simply do anything you please
once you were in the DWMA?
I wish I lived in a world
that knew nothing of the gods.
Whoa, whoa...
...do you seriously mean that?
Of course not...
A world like that
would be... diseased.
[Medusa] I'll say it again,
Professor Stein...
Join my experiment.
This static, unchanging
world doesn't suit you...
You were made
for better than this...
You're a scientist after all.
We can harness the power
of the Kishin together...
We'll change the world
back to what it should be...
...a place where evolution
and progress always reign.
A long time ago...
I was analyzed by a group
of foolish doctors who
feared my violent
tendencies and what they
considered my selfish attitude.
They seemed elated while
they were studying me.
As if they were solving the
crime in a mystery novel.
They'd theorize for hours.
Wondering if something had
traumatized me in my past.
Or if some terrible influence
had come into my life.
That was all nonsense though...
I've loved tearing things apart
from the very beginning.
What's your point, Stein?
Are you trying to compare
me to these doctors?
[Stein]
When I was in kindergarten,
it made me nauseous watching
the other kids as they listened
dutifully to the teacher
and played games.
I would almost puke...
...just from the sight of
everyone focusing
unquestioningly
on the chalkboard while
they took their notes...
not an original
thought in their heads.
What kind of story is
this anyway...?
It's entirely pointless,
not to mention boring...
Makes me want to puke.
Are you mocking me?
If you hate
unoriginality so much,
why are your
attacks so tiresome...?
Really... I'm sleeping here.
Now, now, be more patient...
This is my answer to
your invitation,
so you should listen.
My feelings didn't change.
As I matured and
grew stronger,
the madness inside of me,