[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
Go... eat all you can...
Then eat more.
And more.
[Medusa] Eat as
much as you need to...
Consume everything
in your path...
Until you become
the ultimate evil.
[Crona screams]
♪ opening song ♪
[Soul]
Hello, Italy...!
This is one cool country, huh?
So, what d'ya say...?
Are you getting
hungry, Maka...?
I think it's about time
for some all
you can eat pasta...
Ya know what they say,
"when in Rome,
eat lots of pas--."
We didn't come here to
be tourists or to
stuff our faces...
Do you get that, Soul...?
No... We're in Italy for an
extracurricular lesson, okay?
[Soul] Yeah,
I do know that, Maka...
You didn't have to
scramble my freakin' brains.
[Soul]
Our target this time is
some murderer named
Sonson J, isn't it?
[Maka] So you
were paying attention?
[Soul]
Of course...
This guy likes to lay low
until after dark, right?
[Maka] Nice try, but we're not
sightseeing right now.
We have to gather more
information about the city.
[Soul]
(ugh)... Fine!
[Maka] That's better...
Let's see...
Where can we go
to find some information?
Oh sorry.
[Punk A]
Hey. Hold it, punk.
Problem?
You bet there is...
I got a problem with
any punk who runs in
to me like that.
Who do you think
you're messin' with?
Maybe you'd like me
to show you, huh?
[Soul] If you spoke
more and spit less,
maybe I'd be able
to understand you.
What did small fry say?
Heh... no problem...
If ya don't understand,
we'll explain it to you.
Do you know who
controls this town?
The Materazzi, that's who...
And don't you forget it.
I couldn't care less
about that if I tried.
[Maka] Soul, quit messing
around with these guys.
We've got work to do.
Yeah, fine by me.
I don't think so.
You're not goin' anywhere.
[Soul]
Huh?
[Punk A] If you think you can
cross the Materazzi
and get away with it,
you're stupider than you look.
[Punk B] We'll show ya
what happens to punks.
[Group of punks chuckle]
[Punk A]
Let 'em have it.
[Soul sighs]
[collision]
[Maka] I wonder where we should
go to get some information.
[Soul]
Good question...
We could try that smoke shop
that's around the corner.
[Maka]
Black-Blooded Terror...
There's a Weapon Inside Crona?
[bells toll]
[gothic opera singer]
Now... go and eat your fill...
You are the ultimate creation.
You are perfect...
Weapon and meister
together in one form.
[laughter]
Hey... What's
your deal, pink hair?
[Medusa] Eat their souls,
all of their souls.
[Crona]
No... I can't...
I'm not ready to do it yet.
[Punk A] Hey you...
Didja hear me?
They're not Kishin...
not anywhere close to it.
You listenin'?
I said, what's your deal?
Yeah, freak, and who
are you talking to anyway?
[Medusa]
Nake Snake...
Cobra... Cobra...
[Medusa]
It will be all right...
Have faith in yourself.
Crona... you will be a Kishin.
[Crona chuckles and
builds to a full laugh]
[Crona]
I am a Kishin.
Don't make the mistake
of thinkin' you can walk
into our castle uninvited
and walk out again...
...you dirty punk.
This is a public
place, actually...
The castle doesn't belong
exclusively to you,
or to anyone else
for that matter...
Which is why Ragnarok
is going to eat you all...
Right now...
Ragnarok?
Be-yaaaaaaa!
Ow...! What's up
with that sword?
It's, too loud!
Hey... everybody...
I feel like something
amusing is happening.
The doors here open
only one way.
They open inward.
[Crona laughs]
That thing yesterday
sure was fun, wasn't it?
I don't remember
what it was, though.
Well, no matter.
This much I know...
my blood is black.
[Punks scream]
[Maka]
Found him, finally.
[Sonson J]
More power... more souls.
Listen, you murderous maniac...
Sonson J...
Your soul is mine now....
It's over.
[Maka]
That's the last one we
need to collect
on this trip, right?
[Soul]
Yeah...
And swallowing this soul
is gonna be cooler than
all you can eat pasta.
I was wondering...
Do souls taste good?
You seem to like 'em.
Yeah, they're delicious.
They don't really have
a particular flavor...
It's just the way they
feel goin' down. The texture.
[Maka]
So how do you think
Black Star and
Tsubaki are doing...?
I wonder if they're having
any more luck collecting
souls than usual.
[Soul]
I doubt it...
They're professional losers
when it comes
to soul collecting...
Permanent zeros.
[Maka] I feel bad
for poor Tsubaki.
[Soul] Black Star's energy isn't
directed at soul collecting.
He's more interested in
puffing up his own ego.
Anyway... we're done here.
Let's go...
You can wait
down below for me...
I'll go get the bike
and bring it around.
Hey, Soul, hold on.
Why, is something wrong?
[Maka]
That building.
[Soul] I seem to
remember someone
saying we didn't come
here to sightsee--
oh, that was you!
[Maka]
It's not that.
Something else...
I sense something...
A group of souls all wound
up together over there.
It's all so noisy...
Concentrate... harder.
[Maka] They're all in that
building I pointed to.
I can sense the souls of
a weapon and a meister.
And then there are fifty or
sixty human souls
surrounding them.
Wow, you can tell all
that from over here?
Yeah, it surprised me too...
I think... It looks like
the humans in there...
...are those guys
from this afternoon.
Oh, those idiots again...?
Why do we care what
happens to them?
I don't like them any
more than you do, Soul...
...but they're still human...
They're punks, but it's not
like their souls have
become Kishin eggs.
Let's just forget
about 'em, Maka...
It's Saturday night,
after all...
For all we know, maybe they've
just got a little
fever goin' on.
No, Soul... Now's not
the time for jokes...
We're representatives
of the academy...!
If we ignore it and
something bad happens...
...it'll be too late.
[Soul]
Okay, okay, you win...
We'll check it out.
But if we storm in there
and it ends up being a bunch
of people with Black Star
in the center saying
"welcome to my big show!"...
I'm gonna cry.
[Maka] I only
hope that's all it is.
[Soul]
Here we are...
Looks like we get to do
some sightseeing after all.
I do love gothic architecture;
this is one cool building.
[bell tolls]
Oh no...! Impossible!
Hey... what's wrong?
There's no way...
...not that quickly.
[Soul] Okay, slow down
a second, take a breath...
When you start acting like
this I can't keep up with you.
All gone.
[Soul]
What, the bell...?
Yeah, it stopped.
No, no... I'm talking about
the human souls
that were inside...
They disappeared suddenly...
Now there's just the
weapon and the meister.
[Maka thinks] Something tells me
that we should leave this door
closed and get out of here.
But I can't... I have to know...
As a student of the academy,
it's my duty to find
out what happened.
[doors creak]
[Crona]
You see...
They open one way...
Those doors only open inward.
What the hell...
He's in there all by himself...
What happened to
his weapon partner?
No, there's no way...
Now what?
[Ragnarok]
Lady Medusa...
It looks like two
others have arrived.
[Crona] Keep it down Ragnarok
you need to be quiet now.
[Maka] I'm reading the souls
of a meister and a weapon...
And both of them are
directly in front of us.
Which means...
That meister standing there...
has a weapon inside his body.
[Death Scythe]
I screwed up.
Oh yeah...Maka isn't even
at school right now.
All this risk for nothing...
The only place to see Maka's
here at the academy,
so I came... Sure...
But coming here means
I might run into him.
Franken... Stein!
All I wanted was
to see my daughter!
Instead, I'm staring straight
in the face of danger!
But don't worry, Maka...
Your papa's not
going to back down!
I will overcome this obstacle,
and when I do,
you'll know how
much I love you!
You'll finally understand!
But before I do all that,
I need to have the lovely
school nurse heal my
wounded heart and
give me courage...
Oh yes!
I've been waiting
for you, my angel!
Hurry now and heal
my heart with your
sweet, sweet medical loving.
Kiss my pain away!
[Stein]
Hey there Spirit...
I've been looking for you.
Oh no...! Not Stein!
I don't know what
you want with me,
but all the scars from
your experiments
have finally disappeared!
I'm not afraid of you
anymore, so there...!
(Hah-hah!)
I'm not afraid of anything.
How do you like that, Stein...?
Then... I take it you noticed
that I swapped the middle toe
from your right foot with
the one on your left foot?
Huh?! What, are you nuts...?
How could you do
something like that to me?!
Made you look!
You know, that little
daughter of yours, Maka...
...she's growing
up quickly, huh?
I have to be honest, when I
heard you were getting married,
I wasn't so sure about it.
I thought to myself...
"there's no way this
is gonna work out."
But then... I watched the
two of you together...
and you seemed so close
that I was reassured.
And then I thought...
"Those two have found a
love that is sure
to last forever."
[Death Scythe] Umm...
yeah... about that...
You may not know this yet...
...but Maka's mother and I...
...we actually got
divorced last month....
It's over between us.
I know.
Damn it! I'm gonna kill you,
you heartless patchwork freak!
[Stein]
Oh yeah, one other thing.
It seems the Demon
Sword has turned up.
[Death Scythe]
What?
[Soul] What are you
talking about, Maka?
You're telling me there's
a weapon inside that dude?
[Maka]
Not for long...
It's coming out.
[Crona screams]
[Ragnarok]
(Pea-goo-goo-goo)
(Goo-bee-bee)
That hurts me.
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Stop moving around like that,
you're squeezing me!
Don't poke me! Ow!
Stop already.
Don't push my nose!
You're bruising me!
Stop it now...!
I've had enough already!
[Ragnarok] Now, now,
calm down, Crona...
You're so scary when
you're stressed out like this.
[Maka]
Okay...
...this is getting weird.
You should know that
the hunting of human
souls is strictly forbidden.
Are you students...?
I haven't seen
you at the academy.
At the where...?
What academy...?
Anyway, she said it was
okay to eat the human souls
I don't see what's
wrong with it,
if she said it was okay.
I'm, uh...
I'm not very good
at talking to girls...
They make me nervous.
Never mind that.
Her soul looks tasty.
[Maka] Meisters and their
weapons are not allowed to
collect human souls
for any reason...
We hunt only the souls that
have become Kishin eggs.
Now it's my duty to stop you...
You will not hunt any
more humans, you hear me?
[Ragnarok]
Let's get her, Crona.
It turned into a weapon...
a sword.
[Soul] He's gonna
strike from below!
Stop this!
You're going to start
poking at me also?
[Soul]
You've got 'em now!
[Medusa chuckles]
Did you think you
could cut him in half...?
Oh no... not with a
stroke like that one.
[Maka] Black...?
Black blood?
Yes... That's right.
My blood is black.
What's up with this guy...?
His body's way freaky.
I think I have an idea...
I don't know
how it's possible,
but I think his blood
itself is a weapon.
I was able to cut
through his skin...
but his blood hardened,
and the blade stopped
completely when I
hit his blood vessels.
Well if you're right,
then how do you propose
we go about beating him?
[Maka] None of our
normal attacks will work.
I'm not even sure
Witch Hunter will help...
If only I could shoot my
soul wavelength directly
at him like Black Star does,
I might be able to do
some internal damage.
Otherwise, I have no
idea what to do.
Crona... why are you
taking it so easy? Do something.
It's not like the ones before.
Those were boys. She's a girl.
I'm no good with girls.
What am I supposed
to do with her?
[Medusa laughs]
[Medusa]
How silly...
Kill her, of course.
What's with this guy...?
And who is he
talking to anyway?
Oh okay...
You're saying
I can kill the girl?
I didn't realize that!
But maybe I could
play with her hair first...
Just for a little while.
The doors here open inward...
They only open one way.
Ragnarok.
Screaming Resonance.
Goobee!
[Ragnarok screams]
He's coming Maka...
Guard now!
[Soul cries out]
Soul...!
Stop it!
Are you okay Soul...?
Talk to me!
You don't need to worry
about that right now...
I am your weapon
partner, Maka...
That means I am always
prepared to die
for my meister.
[Maka thinks]
What do I do now?
That screaming causes
vibrations along his blade,
and his blood
hardens so quickly.
I can't do any damage
to him at all...
I can't even guard!
[Maka thinks]
I screwed up.
[Soul] What's
the matter, Maka...?
Quit dodging and
start fighting back!
[Ragnarok screams]
[Soul]
Maka!
[Maka thinks]
But if I do attack...
Then Soul...
I can't use Soul to
block his sword.
The only thing I can
do now is run away!
[Crona laughs]
We're getting out of here
Open up!
That's not going
to work, you know.
You should start paying
attention to the things
other people say.
Oh no!
[Crona] The doors
here only open one way...
They open inward.
Maka...! Stop him now!
But Soul, if I guard
you'll die...!
[Maka]
I screwed up.
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka]
Soul...! Soul!
[Crona] Do all
girls shout this much?
[Soul]
Please open your eyes...!
Soul...! Listen to me!
[Crona] The doors here
only open one way...
They open inward.
[Maka]
I'm sorry!
If I wasn't so weak then
this wouldn't have happened!
[Crona] I don't usually listen
to how people talk...
I don't think I can
deal with this situation.
[Maka] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Medusa the Witch...
The One Who Possesses
a Great Evil Soul?
[Crona] I don't know how to
deal with any of this.