[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Kid] The toilet paper is
folded neatly into a triangle.
Absolutely perfect.
And every frame along the wall
is aligned exactly
with the ground.
Absolutely perfect.
The candles on the left
have burned down to the
same height as the
candles on the right.
Absolutely perfect.
[doors creaking]
[Kid] Balance between
left and right...
Perfect symmetry...
That is what is most
important in this world.
Now it's on to school...
C'mon Liz... Patty... Let's go.
Now you're suddenly
in a big rush to go...?
What's the point in hurrying.
We're already three hours late.
♪ opening song ♪
[bells tolling]
[Stein] What should our
lesson be today, class?
I've got it! Why don't we do
another dissection lab?
[students groan and sigh]
Yeah, uh... Dr. Stein...
If I could point something out--
ever since you
became our teacher,
all we've done
is dissect animals.
Every day.
[Stein]
Oh, but you see, Maka...
Today will be different.
This time our
specimen is infinitely
more interesting than
a mouse or frog...
[Stein]
Are you ready for it...?
Today we'll be poking around
the insides of
this little guy here.
A rare species of cuckoo,
endangered, I believe.
[All] Dissect an
endangered species?!
Umm... Dr. Stein,
I don't think we
can dissect that.
It's really rare--
nearly extinct, you know.
[Stein chuckles]
All the more reason to
dissect one before the
entire species dies off.
[Cuckoo cries out]
He's seriously crazy...
He must be insane...
[Tsubaki sighs]
[Stein]
Tsubaki... Maka...
Why don't I see
Soul and Black Star
up there with you...?
Are they planning to
come to class?
[Maka] They're probably
skipping. Again...
Those two idiots
are hopeless...
Sorry, Tsubaki...
We're switching out...
I'm gonna be Soul's
meister from now on.
[Maka]
Jeez...
...if they want to be
together so much,
maybe they should
just be partners.
Huh...?
What do you think?
No! That can never happen,
do you hear me?
Never, never, never!
[Stein] I guess they'll miss
out on the excitement.
I'm sure that you are
all aware by now...
But a very interesting
new student
will be joining our class today.
[Maka]
The New Student...
Kid's First Day
at the Academy...
Will it be an Entrance
to Remember?
[Black Star bellows]
Listen up...
there's someone who must
be assassinated by
the great Black Star.
[Black Star]
Right now...
...at Death Weapon
Meister Academy...
...one rumor stands
out from the rest...
They say that the son of
Lord Death himself has enrolled.
Everyone's talking
about the new guy
instead of focusing on me...
I'll have to kill him.
Clearly. It's a
good thing you've
got your priorities straight.
When the crap is that damn kid
planning on
getting here, anyway?
[Black Star] I've been waiting
around here for three hours!
[Liz] Would you
look at us now...?
Raised on the streets,
but here we are,
students at the academy...
We've come a long
way, huh, Patty?
[Patty] Yeah...!
It's gonna be freaking awesome!
[Kid] Have you ever seen
such a beautiful building...?
My father's school is
magnificent...!
Perfectly balanced,
perfectly symmetrical.
[Soul]
Hey, are you the new kid
we've been hearing
so much about?
[Kid]
This is my first day.
Are you here to show me around?
[Soul snickers]
You show up three hours late,
and you think I've been
waiting here to
give you a tour...?
If you'd been here at seven
like you're supposed to,
you coulda' looked
around yourself.
What's that...?
What did you say? Seven?
No, it can't be seven...!
Say 'eight' dammit...
Eight is better!
Wha-- huh-?
It's physically impossible to
cut the number seven in half
and make it symmetrical.
It has to be eight instead...
Eight cut in half vertically
or horizontally stays
perfectly symmetrical!
[Kid]
Take it back...
I'm begging you...
Just say eight... Please...
please, please, please.
Um... Dude is there
something wrong with you?
Yes... he's absolutely insane.
[Black Star talks from far
away] Yahoo!
No one is permitted to take
attention away from me...!
[Liz] What is that...?
Some kind of monkey?
Yeah... must be a  monkey.
--I'll kill you anyway...
--Yeah... must be a  monkey.
[Black Star] That's right!
I'm going to kill you
today and then tomorrow...
[Liz] Look up there, Kid...
I think that thing is
yelling something at you.
--"Black Star is a god,"
--Not sure what, though.
"Black Star is the
greatest assassin
who ever lived."
How does that sound, new kid?
Are you scared yet?
[Black Star cries
out as he falls]
[Kid screams]
Face it, kid.
I'm much too big
of a guy for you to handle,
and you know it...
Do you see how the very
ground shakes beneath my feet?
Look what you did.
It's not symmetrical
anymore, you jerk.
(ugh)... Nice...
Now you've really done it.
[Patty] Ooohhh!!
[Black Star] Are
you ready for this...?
I'm gonna give you a taste
of my Black Star
assassin skills!
It's not an assassination
if you've been seen idiot.
You are a disgusting pig...
Are you really so eager to
risk your soul that you'll
pick a fight with a Grim Reaper?
[Kid] Liz... Patty...
Weapon forms.
Rii-iight!
We've done nothing but
fight since we
got off the streets.
I could use a break.
[Black Star] If you wanna fight
let's do it. C'mon Soul!
[Soul] You're the one who's
looking for a fight,
Black Star, not me.
I'll play along...
But I'm warning you new guy,
if we do this you'll lose.
Damn straight...
We're gonna make one
badass team together.
[Soul thinks] This guy
was strong enough
to bring down Anubis.
[Black Star thinks]
He's gotta have guts
to try and outshine
me all the time.
[Kid thinks] These two punks
may not be perfect...
...but they did manage to
defeat Sid and hold off
Dr. Stein's attacks.
I'll need to keep my guard up.
Let's go.
[gunfire]
Hey what...?
[Student 1]
Dr. Stein...
It's Soul and Black Star...
They're fighting
someone outside.
[Stein] Hmm?
[Maka] Soul, that idiot...
What is it now?
Excuse me Dr. Stein ...
There's a rule
about two meisters
dueling on campus...
It states that, in order for
the duel to continue,
there must be a professor
there to witness it.
I hate to stop here,
but it can't be helped.
[Cuckoo nervously cries out]
We'll have to
postpone the dissection.
As Soul and
Black Star's partners,
Maka and Tsubaki,
come along with me.
Everyone else study something.
We can't even get
close to the guy.
What was that...?
You're looking for a more up
close and personal fight...?
Fine by me.
[Black Star thinks]
We'll see.
[Soul cries out as he attacks]
Damn it!
What the hell?
[gun fires]
Oh man, that hurt
really, really bad!
Did you think a pair of
normal pistols would be
enough for a Grim Reaper?
We aren't like regular
guns that shoot bullets...
We shoot compressed wavelengths
of our meister's soul...
[Soul thinks]
Damn it.
[Black Star thinks]
How dare he go easy on us?
[Stein]
Oh, my...
They probably should have
picked a different opponent.
Dr. Stein, is that the boy...?
The one with the guns.
Is he the new
kid that everyone's
been talking about so much?
Yep...
That's Lord Death's son...
Death the Kid...
It was his own decision
to attend the academy...
But he won't be
a normal student...
His abilities are far greater
than anyone else's here.
[Tsubaki thinks]
But why Black Star?
Sorry, Tsubaki...
We're switching out...
I'm gonna be Soul's
meister from now on.
[Maka]
Tsubaki...?
Is something wrong?
Oh no, it's nothing.
[Stein] My dear soul-seeing
Scythe Meister Maka,
can I borrow you for a moment?
Uh, yeah...?
[Stein] I have a special lesson
in mind for you today.
[Maka]
Oh... okay.
[Stein] Now, now... there's
no reason to be worried...
It's a very simple question.
Take a look at the duel.
Watch Kid and his
twin pistols as they fight...
I want you to
pay particular attention
to their souls' wavelengths.
[Maka] Normally
it's almost impossible
to sync the wavelengths
of two weapons like that...
But the connection between
all three of them is
strong and very stable.
[Maka] And the weapons seem
to share a respect for him...
No, that's not the word.
Admiration... is that it?
Exactly correct...
a good observation...
The twin pistols are
called the Thompson sisters.
They grew up on the streets...
Their lives were much
harder before they met Kid...
It's natural they would have
a strong admiration for him.
[Stein] The partnership
works for Kid, too.
It's good for him to
be around people so different...
The Thompson sisters' laid-back
attitudes have
a positive influence
on him by quieting
his neurotic tendencies.
They do make a really
good team, those three.
Don't they?
You can't even compare
'em to our two idiots out there.
Let's hurry up and
finish this guy off.
It's about time.
[Kid]
For what?
You should quake with fear
of your impending death!
When you say that,
it just makes me want to laugh.
You won't be laughing when
you taste our
"Power of Friendship."
That's right...
It's incredible...
The power is beyond belief.
What?
Let's do it.
Yeah.
[Soul]
Transform!
Whoa!
That's so cool!
I don't think they're
taking this very seriously.
Come on, Soul!
[Soul]
Friendship!
[Black Star]
Fusion!
[split]
[Soul] Why the hell did you
catch me with your head, moron!?
Ah! I don't know!
[Soul]
Do it right this time.
You're too freaking heavy...!
I can't pick you up.
[Soul]
I'm not heavy.
Maka swings me around
without breaking a sweat.
Black Star and Soul
are definitely
lacking in the compatible
wavelength department.
So it seems.
[Black Star]
Come on, you stupid scythe...!
I just need to lift you up.
What the hell are you
doing hitting me with
your soul's wavelength?
That hurt, you idiot!
[Black Star]
Oh... my bad.
It's almost hard to
watch... Those morons can't
seem to sense each other's
wavelengths at all.
Before a meister and his or
her weapon fight an opponent,
they need to adjust their
wavelengths to each other.
[Soul] Black Star...
It's over between us.
Wh-What exactly are
you saying, Soul?
[Soul] If we try to stay
together like this...
I'll only end up hating
you... It's for the best.
[Maka and Tsubaki]
Huh?
[Stein]
[Kid] Hey...
can I shoot them now?
[Liz] Let's wait. Things are
just starting to get good.
Oh... I understand...
but even though it's over...
Would it be okay...
...if we stay friends?
[Soul]
You idiot...!
Of course we're still
going to be friends. Forever!
Oh Soul!
Black Star!
They need professional help.
[gunfire]
[Kid]
Oops. Sorry.
My fingers slipped.
We can't just quit in
the middle of a fight.
Right...! We're not giving
up 'til we beat him.
Kay... We'll see how
well that works.
[Soul and Black Star
bellow as they attack]
[Black Star] Let's see how you
handle a taste of my soul waves.
[Maka] Black Star's
specialty is martial arts...
...but Kid is just
playing with him.
And the way he's
been fighting today,
Soul has no chance
against him either.
[Kid] You're as low
as you are stupid.
You're going down!
You idiot, you fell for it.
Hah...! Gotcha!
[Black Star weakly]
Okay...
Now I really
wanna kill that guy.
Our partners are
pretty useless, huh?
And now it's time...
...to see the power
of a Grim Reaper.
Let's go! Soul Resonance!
Huh...? It looks like their
souls have begun to expand.
Now they're showing
off their true strength.
Okay...! Let's see what
you've got, huh?
"Reaper Shmeaper!" Bring it on!
Execution mode, ready.
Prepare to die.
Um... I don't
like the looks of that.
Come on, what're
you gonna do, little man?!
I've swatted flies
scarier than you...!
So there!
[Liz]
Resonance stable...
Noise at zero
point three percent.
[Patty] Black Needle
soul wavelength--
fully charged.
[Liz]
Preparing to fire...
Feedback in four seconds.
Three.
[Patty]
Two.
One.
Firing now!
[Kid]
Death... Cannon.
This doesn't look good...!
We should run.
Hah...! Don't be ridiculous.
No way is something like
that gonna hurt me!
That's impossible!
[explosion]
Black Star!
Oh man. What were
those idiots thinking?
Looks like a decisive defeat.
[Stein thinks] But... you can
hardly expect anything less
from the son of
the Grim Reaper.
His potential is great...
and already far above that
of any other meister
at the academy.
And somehow I have a
feeling that he still isn't
showing us everything he can do.
Lord Death's very
own flesh and blood...
What I wouldn't give
to study that one.
[Patty]
Aye-yai-yai.
Great, here we go again.
[Stein]
What happened to him?
Not much.
It's just a little cut.
What got cut?
I think I might have
an idea of what it was.
[Maka] Well... I'm pretty sure
it happened during
Soul's last attack on kid...
I think that Kid got a
little hair cut off
from his bangs.
After the explosion happened
and things died down...
Kid finally noticed that
one side of his bangs was
shorter than the other...
His symmetry was off,
so he spit up
blood and fell over.
He's the one bleeding now,
so that means we actually
won the fight, huh?
Yeah, right...
It means we won, and I,
Black Star, have
defeated the Reaper...!
I knew it! ...Who's going to be
talking about this guy now?!
[Black Star laughs]
Are you really sure
you're all right now,
Black Star?
Hell yeah,
of course I'm all right...
I beat Death today!
I'm awesome!
[Tsubaki]
Yeah... It was amazing.
[Maka]
Hey.
Don't let yourself get involved
in stupid fights, all right?
Come on...
That's exactly what
you used to tell me, Soul.
Yeah, I guess I was the
uncool one of us today, huh?
[Tsubaki] Please try not to do
anything too crazy from now on.
Yeah, right...
Nothing's too
crazy for me now...
I've beaten up
a Reaper, after all.
What's crazier than that?
[Maka] Tsubaki's the
only one for him.
I don't think anyone else
could handle Black Star.
[Soul] Yeah...
...you're probably right.
[Maka]
Coming?
Yeah.
[Soul]
Sorry.
[Maka] Let's stay cool, okay?
[Soul]
You got it.
[Death]
What's up...? Whassup...?
Whaaaazzzup?
Hi there Lord Death!
[Death]
So, I heard my son had
an eventful first
day at school...
Kid can be
difficult sometimes...
I hope no one's hurt too badly.
[Maka thinks]
I wonder...
What does the soul of
Lord Death look like?
I'll take a look.
[Maka thinks] Huh...?
I can't see it.
[Death]
All right, everyone...
I'm going to go ahead
and take Kid home now...
I think he could use
a little rest... Byyyee!
[Black Star]
Right! See ya later.
[Maka thinks]
I don't understand...
Kid's his son,
and he has a soul...
I saw it with my own eyes...
Why can't I see Lord Death's?
[Soul]
Hey...! Maka!
What are you doing
standing around like that...?
Let's go back inside.
[Maka]
Yeah, okay.
I guess it's possible that
Lord Death just
doesn't have a soul.
[Maka]
Oh well... Whatever.
♪ closing song ♪
[Soul] Hey you, why are
you glaring at me?
Come over here and
I'll punch you in the face.
[Maka] These boys
seem so angry...
I don't think they
can even control it.
[Soul]
Vroom! Vroom!
No one can stop me
when I decide to go wild...!
Oh, crap! It's the cops!
Quick-- distract 'em!
[Maka] Joy-riding,
brawling, dueling...
every day, they seem to get into
more trouble than the last...
But maybe a little romance
will slow 'em down...
I guess we'll see.
[Soul] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Black-blooded Terror...
There's a Weapon
Inside Chrona...?
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul.