[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Eruka]
The guard's fast asleep...
Perfect.
[Free] Who's there...?
Talk to me.
[Eruka] I... I was sent here
by someone who wants
to break you out of
that cell and free
you from witch prison...
I'm gonna let you
out now okay.
What kinda person
do you think I am...?
You think I take handouts
from whoever comes along?
[Free]
Thank you!!
[Eruka]
Sure thing. No problem.
It's easy to get outta there
when you got someone
on the outside with a key.
But you wanna know
what I was gonna try
before you showed up?
I had a plan!
Never mind that.
We need to hurry.
They'll be coming after us.
See, I was planning
to try that thing they
do in the movies...
You know, where they
tunnel under the wall
by using a spoon to
steadily dig away at
the ground underneath it...?
I always thought that
was a really cool idea
when they did that...
So...decided I would
give it a try myself...
But all they ever gave
me was chopsticks!
[Free cries out]
[Free]
You can't dig with those...!
I tried to think of
another way out...
I thought about it
all the time...
...then I realized something...
I'm just not an idea man.
[Eruka] I suppose it
doesn't matter now,
but you could have
peed on the bars of
your cell everyday...
and gradually corroded
them away, right?
Oh, damn it!?
Why didn't I try that?
I'm such an idiot.
We have to hurry!
They're coming after us...!
If your hands and feet
are still shackled like that,
you can't fight and we'll--
Be careful...
I smell someone nearby.
They're already here!
Listen up Prisoner Thirteen...
Man with the Magic Eye...
If you resist,
we'll show you no mercy.
[Free] I was locked inside that
prison for two hundred years.
If you think I'm gonna
let you take me back there
without putting up a fight...
Hah... Then you're all crazy.
Oh no...! This is really bad...!
If I don't get you out of here,
then I'm gonna
end up dead too!
Calm down...
It'll take more than
that to kill me...
You should know that.
Damn!
Don't!
[Free]
You think the Grandwitch
kept me alive all this
time just for fun?
She couldn't kill me.
See, that would've
been tough considering...
...I'm immortal.
[guards cry out]
♪ opening song ♪
[Stein]
Thanks for coming...
Are you two ready
to get started?
Not until you explain
to me what we're doing
at school on a Sunday.
I asked him to give us some
special lessons, okay...?
That's why.
This rooom's got a
funny smell to it,
dontcha think?
It's the scented candles.
[Stein]
Let's get started.
But first I want
to warn you both...
Your lesson today will
be extremely dangerous.
Failing it could result in
permanent damage to you.
If that happens,
you may never be able
to match soul wavelengths again.
Do you want to
back down now...?
It's not too late.
No... We'll still do it.
Hey!
Your meister has
made a decision...
Now accept it.
Why are you so
anxious to do this Maka?
Fine. Let's begin then...
Turn around so that
you're facing each other.
Now tell your partner
what his or her flaws are.
Our special lesson is
insulting each other?!
[Stein]
Yes, you could say that.
You're stubborn and reckless.
All you like to do
for fun is read,
so you're boring.
And you have fat ankles.
That's another one...!
You always hit me...
That's a flaw, all right.
[Soul] Professor... is beating
me up part of the lesson?
[Stein] No more
beating on Soul, Maka.
[Stein] This may seem like a
meaningless training
exercise to them,
but these are
no ordinary candles...
They're designed to
heighten a person's emotions.
With these burning,
even a casual remark
could ruin their friendship.
But, if they can
get beyond this,
they will be better for it...
Their soul wavelengths will
resonate even more
strongly than before.
What's going on?
You've been acting
weird lately...
You never even asked
if I wanted to do this lesson...
I wanna know what
this is really about.
This is about me getting
stronger so I can keep you
from getting hurt
that badly ever again.
The meister fights in order
to make the weapon stronger.
You know that...
You wanna get stronger
in order to protect your weapon.
That's all backwards.
You're crazy.
Crazy...?!
And why shouldn't
I want to be stronger?
I hate having to be
protected by you, Soul!
Don't yell so loud...
It's annoying me.
[Maka]
I'll shout if I want to.
You're the one
who's crazy, Soul.
Why are you so against
me getting stronger?!
[Demon] You're going to
need more power.
Power so overwhelmingly
strong you can say
goodbye to all your fears.
Find a rule to break.
It will make you stronger
than you thought possible.
[Soul thinks] I'm not afraid
of that little demon.
I'm not afraid of
becoming stronger, either.
Forget about it,
and sit down, will ya...?
You're hurting my neck.
I won't!
[Stein thinks]
This isn't good.
Their soul wavelengths...
Are beginning to slip.
[Maka]
The Man With the Magic Eye
~Soul and Maka's
Diverging Soul Wavelength?~
You did it?
Uh-huh...
I brought the guy.
Good work, Eruka.
I've done my part...
Now take all your
snakes out of my body
like you promised you would.
All...? Oh, no...
You must be joking...
I'll remove one snake
for every errand you run.
Huh...? How many more
of them are there?
That's not something
you need to know right now...
Of course, I could bring
them all out at once...
You'd be ripped apart
in the process, though.
That's awful...!
How could you devil woman?!
[Free] You're the one
who set me free?
I wouldn't have
expected it from a witch.
Yes, I'm Medusa...
Nice to meet you...
Man with the Magic Eye.
Man with the Magic Eye, huh?
Of course...
What else could you
call me, after all...?
In that prison, even my
name was taken away from me.
But as of today,
I'm officially free again...
All right, then...
My new name is "Free."
Yes, that's right...
You're Free.
[Medusa laughs]
Free, huh...? We'll have to
see about that, won't we?
I owe ya one...
I'd like to
repay you somehow.
No, no... That's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Please let me.
I like to settle my debts.
Well maybe...
...there is one thing
I could ask you to do for me...
There's a certain weapon
and meister pair
I would like to see crushed.
From the DWMA...
That what you mean?
Yes.
I don't like Death or
that school of his...
With all his damn rules...
You've got a deal witch...
I'll take 'em out.
[Black Star]
Hello, London...!
Black Star has arrived... Yahoo!
It's snowing...
Aren't you freezing?
[Black Star]
Who cares about snow...?
Snow can't touch me...!
I could be naked out here
and it wouldn't
bother me at all.
This whole thing sucks...
Ever since Soul got himself
hurt by that Demon Sword,
all our extra lessons
have to be done with
at least two teams...
You guys better not
slow me down okay?
Hey you two, would you
come take a look at this?
It's so beautiful at night,
don't you think...?
Huh? Yay! London!
[Black Star]
What's with them?
Anyway, Maka...
I can't detect souls,
so this one's up to you.
Tell us what you see.
[Maka]
I'm on it.
'Kay, let's see...
I'm focusing in on any
souls that are in this area...
There's one right there.
Hey, you're right...
What does that dude want?
I don't know...
Something's wrong
with his soul...
It's not normal...
There's a bunch of
stuff all mixed together.
Some human...
...some witch...
...and I'm sensing
something else too.
Here you are.
This guy wants a fight...
Looks like our lesson is
getting off to a good start.
Be careful, though...
He's probably able
to use magic.
[Black Star] Tsubaki,
Enchanted Sword Mode...
Let's finish
this guy off quickly.
But you still
can't handle that one.
I just have to last
for a few seconds... let's go!
Yeah...Right!
Impressive... he's strong.
Let's go Soul Resonance!
Amazing...!
Their resonance
is still stable...
...and is that...
...Black Star's soul?!
[Black Star] London Bridge
is falling down dude.
[Free]
Wolf Wolves...
Ice Cone!
Tsubaki!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
What!?
She stopped it
with her shadow!
How about a taste of
my new technique?
Shadow Star!
[echoes]
Star...Star...Star...
Star...Star.
I told you it was
too much for you!
[Soul] He didn't
even last ten seconds.
Black Star might be
strong, all right...
but he's still crazy.
Now then, who's next?
[Soul] You shouldn't drop
your guard like that Mister.
He got 'em... No...!
Soul, get outta there!
It happens a lot...
but fortunately,
I can afford to
let my guard down.
What's with this guy...?
What's he doing?
Look at that!
His wound's closing up!
Of course it's closing up...
What else would it do?
I am immortal.
This guy is an immortal?
[Free] Maybe it would help if
you could see my true form?
What do you mean,
'your true form'?
[Free begins to growl
as he powers up]
What's happening
to the shape of his soul...?
It's changing!
I know who he is now...
We've run into
the legendary wolfman...
...the one who stole
the witch's eye!
[Free bellows]
Now, Soul...
It's time to transform!
Yeah!
Okay, Soul. Let's go.
[Soul]
Right!
Ow!
What are you doing Maka?!
Your handle's too hot.
I can't hold you.
What!?
It's like before...
That time when Black Star
and Soul were fighting Kid.
Black Star tried to lift
Soul but couldn't.
And this time,
Soul's handle burned Maka.
I don't think their
soul wavelengths are in sync.
[Medusa laughs]
[Medusa]
Poor Soul Eater,
with all that black
blood still inside of you...
...how are you and your
precious meister Maka
going to handle this
turn of events, I wonder?
And so...
the experiment begins.
[Maka thinks]
So... difficult... to breathe...
Why is this happening...?
How do I breathe, again...?
Just inhale
and exhale, right...?
And how do I use my weapon?
Fighting Wolf Fist...Let's go!
[Soul]
Maka!
Ice Cylinder!
Soul!
[Free]
Magic Eye Cannon.
Damn it. That was not good...
I always forget not to
put those things where
they can skewer me.
But it's okay...
No problem at all,
nothing to see here...
After all...
...I'm immortal.
He's an immortal...
magic... werewolf...
I can't deny that this
guy is strong,
but he sure is... clumsy.
I guess sitting in a
witch prison for
two hundred years
would make anyone rusty...
I can't seem to handle my
magic as well as I used to.
Maka... We have to do something.
If you can't use Soul,
try fighting with me.
It won't work...
Even if I could figure out
how to use you in time...
I still wouldn't be
able to defeat him.
[Free]
You meisters...
The great Lord Death
plays by his own rules...
It's those rules that decide...
what evil is.
What are you talking about?
[Free] You all follow
the reaper so blindly...
What gives him the right
to decide how the
world should be run?
He trains you to hunt down souls
he believes are unworthy.
A soul like mine wouldn't
be safe from him.
But I for one am not
going to accept that
kind of future...
I refuse.
It's my turn now.
I'm gonna be the judge.
I'm not goin' play
by his rules anymore.
Maka!
[Maka]
Soul...
Transform back into a scythe.
Wait, Maka...
...you couldn't even
hold me before.
Do it!
[Tsubaki] Using a weapon when
your wavelengths aren't
in sync is incredibly hard on
the mind as well as the body...
But what else can she do...?
Maka is a scythe meister,
and Soul is her weapon.
Maka... Your hands...
[Maka thinks]
I'm going to become...
...stronger!
Take this!
You'll have to do
better than that.
How's this?
Damn!
What are you doing...?
Calm down, take a breath.
Stay out of it...
I'm going to do this.
I refuse to let him defeat me!
[Soul]
Don't be an idiot!
If shouting like a
spoiled brat made
you stronger,
everyone would do it!
[Maka]
Shut up...!
It's because of you
saying stuff like that
that our wavelengths
are out of sync.
That's not cool, Soul.
It isn't cool at all!
[Demon]
Gain power...
I can show you
how if you need.
Shut your mouth, Maka!
What do you even know, anyway?!
That is enough, you two!
[Tsubaki]
You guys are a team...
You have to work
together if you
want to do anything...
One person can't make
a decision without the other...
You decide together...
and you fight together.
[Soul] Right, like Black Star
stops to consult you
every time he's about
to do something stupid?
[Tsubaki] I'll admit
Black Star makes
some dumb calls
from time to time.
But the important thing is,
I'm here to back him
up no matter how
big a fool he is....
If we're fools,
we're fools together.
That's the kind of team we are.
[Maka thinks]
Maybe Tsubaki's right...
I want to become stronger...
but there's no reason
I have to do it alone...
All I've been thinking
about this whole time was
catching up to Soul somehow.
No matter how hot
it gets, I'm not letting go.
Soul and I are going
to grow stronger together.
[Soul] I don't get what you've
been so worried about...
I'm not even all that strong.
If you're done telling me
what to do, maybe we can
work together now.
[Soul]
Hey, Demon guy...
You can lead me
wherever you want...
Let's hear your plan...
...and we'll see
whether I follow it.
In that case, come with me.
Overwhelming madness
and power await.
You... got it.
Let's go Soul Resonance!
Excellent...... finally...
...the black blood is
starting to do its work.
Wow...!
Their soul resonance
rate is incredible.
[Maka thinks]
What's happening?
Something's wrong...
Is Soul devouring me?
This should be interesting.
A weapon with black blood
has the power to
swallow its meister's mind...
Now... let's see you raise
your resonance rate even higher.
[Soul]
Damn! It feels like my
consciousness
is being carried away.
I won't let it...
I will stay in control.
The legendary super
skill of the scythe meister.
Witch Hunter!
A fancy technique...
Fine by me...
Wolf Wolves,
Wolf Wolves, Wolf Wolves.
Wolftail Wall!
We can get past that.
[Maka thinks]
It doesn't hurt; it's not hot;
I'm not scared...
I will not be beaten!
I won't ever let
Soul get hurt again!
I'm going to get stronger!
Figure-6 Hunter!
What the hell?!
We get him?
Almost there.
A meister throwing her weapon
aside and attacking?
Maka!
[Maka bellows]
Down you go!
Soul...
I guess...your ankles...
aren't that fat.
Maka!
If you think I'm falling
all by myself, think again...
I'm taking you with me.
[Soul]
Maka... Damn!
There's no way
I'm letting you go.
[Black Star]
Yahoo!
It's a good thing I'm
here to look out for you two.
This isn't over yet...
Wolf Wolves, Wolf Wolves,
Wolf Wolves.
I'll just make an ice cylinder
under my feet, kick off it,
and fly back up there...
I can do that, right...?
Of course I can...!
I'm immortal!
I can do whatever I want!
Ice Cylinder!
Wrong place again.
A truly impressive
screw up, even for him.
[Free] My first fight in
two hundred years,
and I screwed it up...
I'll get it right next time,
I just need some practice...
Yeah... just a little practice.
[Medusa thinks] I've seen
enough to convince me...
If I continue my research
on black blood,
I am certain
I can create a Kishin.
Are you sure you're
gonna be all right?
Yeah I'm fine, thanks.
From the way your hands look,
I'm guessing I'll be the
one on cooking duty
for a while, huh?
That oughta be interesting.
[Maka]
Black... blood?
♪ closing song ♪
[Soul] Well,
we survived our lesson...
Black Star, what d'ya say
we go grab some
boring English food?
[Black Star] Let's find
someplace with karaoke too.
I feel a star moment coming on.
[Soul] So, should we eat
fish and chips or...
...fish and chips?
[Black Star] Food,
karaoke, then sightseeing!
[Soul]
If we're feeling crazy,
we could try some
bangers and mash.
[Black Star]
I'm kinda tired.
Maybe I'll just go
home and watch t.v.
[Soul] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
The Super Written Exam...
Heart-pounding, Reeling,
and Restless, You're Kidding?
[Soul and Black Star] What...?!
We have a test next week?!
[Soul] Ah, man that
spoiled my appetite.
No Yorkshire pudding for me.