[Maka] A sound soul...
...dwells within a
sound mind...
and a sound body.
[Narrator] Welcome to Death
Weapon Meister Academy...
...more commonly known
as the DWMA.
It stands as a defense
against the forces of evil,
which would plunge the world
into chaos and drag humanity
to the very depths of
fear and madness--
the demons known as Kishin,
and their insatiable
hunger for destruction...
To ensure the Kishin
never regain their hold
on this world, this academy
was founded by the
Grim Reaper, Death himself.
[Death]
So basically...we're an
organization that exists to
protect and preserve peace.
I guess it's not
exactly a typical school...
Oh well, that isn't important...
For now, let's roll up
our sleeves and get to work!
♪ opening song ♪
[bell tolls]
[footsteps]
[Jack emits a growl]
[Woman 2 screams]
[Jack]
Want...more...power...
[Woman 2 makes panic sounds]
[Jack]
More... power. Power!
[Woman 2 softly cries
out then footsteps]
That man, Soul Eater...
His soul...
Yeah Maka, there's no
doubt about it.
That dude's soul is
a Kishin Egg. It's pure evil.
He's not human anymore.
[Maka]
Any soul that breaks from
the path of humanity
and becomes evil...
runs the risk of
transforming into a Kishin.
In the name of Lord Death,
this evil must be purged...
Let's collect the damaged
soul and end this.
[Soul] Just so
we're clear, Maka...
This guy's turning himself
into a weapon.
He's the same as me that way...
...'course I look a lot cooler
in my human form than he does.
But being a weapon isn't
what the problem is here...
The problem with
this guy... is his soul.
[Maka]
I know.
You! Serial Killer,
Jack the Ripper--
Your murdering
days are done...
Your soul is mine!
[Jack growls]
[Maka] Weapon and Meister--
two fighting as one.
Let's go, Soul Eater.
[Maka] It's ours now...
the 99th soul.
Maka, thank you
for a good meal.
We're almost there aren't we...?
Took us long enough,
but that was number
ninety-nine.
So we've finally
collected all the
Kishin souls we need.
Only one thing left now.
I've just gotta eat the
soul of a witch...
then I'll be one of
Lord Death's weapons...
You're lookin' at the
next Death Scythe.
I know... as if I wasn't
cool enough already, right?
[Maka] Anyway... we'd
better report back
to Lord Death and let him know.
Just write in the
Death Room's number...
"Forty-two, Forty-two,
Five-sixty-four: whenever
you want to knock
on Death's door."
[Maka] Hello, Lord Death,
are you there?
Meister Maka reporting.
[Death] Ya ya...!
Hello, Meister Maka...
How are you doing?
How did it go?
I've just collected the
99th Kishin soul, sir...
Now we just have one witch
soul left to collect
and we'll be done.
Well done, Maka...
You're proving to be
just as excellent a meister
as your mother was.
[Maka giggles]
[Death Scythe]
Hey...! Soul Eater!
If you even think of
touching my Maka...
if you lay a hand on her,
as a Death Scythe... no...
...as her father,
I will freakin' kill you.
Ya got me,
ya little octopus head?
What are you smoking...?
See how cool I am...?
You think I'm gonna settle for
a flat-chested girl like her?
What did you just say?!
Are you trying to tell me
that my Maka's not attractive?!
Why haven't you
made a move on her,
you're a man, aren't you?
You know you're a
little annoying.
Maka... your dad loves you.
(Humph) Don't waste
your breath on me.
There's no way I'll
ever consider you my father.
[Death] Enough of that...
Let's set the family feud
aside for a moment...
As you know...if a meister
and weapon pair collect
ninety-nine evil souls...
souls that have strayed
and become Kishin Eggs...
and additionally collect the
soul of one witch...
then the weapon will
obtain the qualifications
necessary to become
a Death Scythe...
one of my instruments.
But it's that last soul
that's a bit tricky.
You've made it this far...
but you should know...
there are countless meisters
who have lost their lives
when they challenged a witch.
You'll need to be
very careful, Maka...
But if you're lucky,
maybe the Death Scythe
you create will be as powerful
as the one your mom
created before you.
Right!
[Death] Also... please do be
sure not to make any mistakes.
This last collection,
the witch's soul,
is very important...
If you slip up,
all of the ninety-nine
Kishin souls the two of you
have collected so far
will be confiscated.
[Maka] We understand, sir.
Yeah we'll make a
clean job of it, no worries.
[Death] In that case,
I'll see you two later.
[Death Scythe]
Maka!
[Death]
You are a bit annoying.
Maka!
[whack]
If you don't shut up,
I'm going to use my
[Death] Reaper Chop to split
your head open.
[Death Scythe]
It's more effective if
you warn before you chop.
[Maka]
Resonance of the Soul
Will Soul Eater
Become A Death Scythe?
[Blair] "Pum pum pumpum.
I always get what I want.
Just give it to me
Pum pum pumpum.
I'm a beauti--
beauti-ful, pret-ty lady."
Come give my back a scrub.
But ya know, ya know...
I've got a secret, yes I do.
Pumpkins! Pum-pum-pumkin,
pum-pum-pumkin!
'Cause that's my magic spell!
Pum-pum-pumkin,
pum-pum-pumkin! Yeah...
[Maka] This must be the house
where the witch Blair lives.
[Soul] A pumpkin house...?
That's cool.
It looks tasty but sneaking
into a house isn't very manly...
Why don't we just
charge right in there?
We can't. She's different from
the others we've faced so far.
Let's go!
Hey...! Come back here!
Naked lady!
Hey, what's the matter?
Is everything okay down
there in the bubbles,
little boy?
It's okay. Cool guys see
naked women all the time.
I'm totally used to it.
Of course you are dear.
I'm sure that's why
your nose is bleeding.
Yeah. Nevermind.
Your soul is mine--
[Maka] You idiot...!
What were you thinking?!
Sorry to interrupt...
...but I'll be taking
your soul now.
I hope that cute boy
will be all right...
Wha--
Could you transform
into a scythe?
Working on it, Maka.
Okay, that's it, witch lady...
Naked or not,
I'm still gonna
eat your soul now.
Witch lady?
Oh, wow...!
He really became a scythe.
After I take your soul,
he'll be much more...
Soul will be a Death Scythe.
And I'll have created a
weapon stronger than my dad!
[Blair[
I like it.
Why don't you be a good
little girl and give it to me.
Pumpkin, pumpkin, pumpkin...
Halloween Cannon!
[Death Scythe laughs]
[Lisa]
Wow, Death Scythe...
...you're a real
frisky one, aren't you?
Oh, and I heard that
you have a little daughter, too.
Isn't that right?
What sort of girl is she?
You don't wanna ask that...
Trust me on this one.
Kay... but why?
Just in case you haven't
figured it out yet,
Death Scythe is
a bit of a player...
and that didn't go over
very well with his wife.
Huh...
They're in the process
of getting a divorce right now.
The worst thing is his
daughter Maka, is on her
mother's side. She hates him!
That sounds complicated...
Maka!
Please don't hate me, Maka!
I love you and Mama...!
I promise, Maka...!
It's true! It's true...!
I love you...!I love you!
Thank you very much, sir.
[Lisa and Arisa]
Bye, Mister Death Scythe!
Please come again!
[Death Scythe]
Yeah. [PAUSE]  Bye!
[Soul]
Damn that witch...!
How am I supposed to be cool
when she's all hot and
naked like that, huh?
We expected a stiff attack.
She is a witch.
But you lost your chance to
become a death scythe because
you couldn't resist her.
You're just jealous
of her boobs.
[Soul]
It's her. What now?
[Maka]
I'm thinking.
Ah! My little scythe-ey boy!
[Maka] Listen up, Soul...!
This time I wrote down
a detailed plan on this
piece of paper.
And that's supposed to
give us an edge this time?
We aren't exactly going
grocery shopping here.
A piece of paper isn't gonna
help us beat a witch.
Fine, then you tell me
what we need to
do to beat Blair!
Who knows?
I vote for brute force, though.
That's your answer
for everything!
We have to work together here,
or don't you wanna
become a Death Scythe?
--You have to take
--Yeah, I get it, Maka...
--this seriously, Soul!
--You can shut up now.
[Maka] This is a witch we're
going up against!
--Let's just follow my--!
--[Blair] Pumkin... Pum-Pumkin
--[Maka and Soul] Hmm?
--[Blair] Halloween cannon!
[explosion]
[Blair laughs]
You should give it up...
You can't beat me, girl.
[Soul] What are you
doing, you idiot?
[Maka]
Shut up!
Or were you just gonna try
beating her by getting
a nosebleed again?
Men are completely
useless sometimes...
You only ran into Blair's
house in the first place
because you knew
she was taking a bath!
Now you're just
making false accusations...!
And would you tell me
how girls always come up
with these wild assumptions
in the first place?!
Women's intuition.
[Soul] I don't understand
you sometimes.
Hey there, little scythe boy...
is that dumb girl of yours
giving you a hard time?
Why don't you forget about
her and come be mine...?
I would never, ever yell at you
like she is no matter
what you did to me.
[Maka]
Hold on, witch!
I'm Soul's partner,
not you, okay...?
Our conversations
don't concern you.
[Blair]
Hmmmm...Is that so?
Well...We'll see
about that, girlie.
What the--
[Blair] Pum-Pumpkin, pumpkin...
Smashing Pumpkin!
[explosion]
[Maka cries out]
What should we try now, Soul...?
My attacks won't work on her!
Soul?
Soul? Hello...?
What's wrong?
Why don't you forget about
her and come be mine?
[Death Scythe chuckles]
Hah...!
Good times at Chupa Cabra's.
You're out drinking when
your daughter's in trouble...?
What kind of father are you?
[Death Scythe]
What? Maka...?!
Something happened?
[Death] She's not doing so
well against this witch...
It looks like she might die.
What? Maka, hold on!
[Death]
Stop right there...
Think about what
you're doing...
You or I could win against
an opponent like
that with one blow...
A single Reaper Chop is
all it would take
to crush her skull...
We both know that, Death Scythe.
But our skills aren't
being tested right now.
You're her father...
You must understand
the situation.
Maka.
[Death] Still...There's
something a little
weird about that witch.
[explosion followed
by Maka bellowing]
Soul, what's going on?
I don't understand why
you haven't been answering me!
[Soul]
Maka...
There you are.
Stop talking.
Hey, what did you
drop me like that for?!
I don't think we should
be partners anymore Maka...
You see... I only want to be
Witch Blair's weapon now!
Oh! Do you really want me?
Yeah, that's more like it...
Leave my daughter alone,
ya little scumbag!
Is now really the time
to be saying that?
Blair! You used your magic
to make Soul want to
be with you.
That's a dirty trick!
[Soul]
You really are stupid...
Any man would choose a girl
with a body like Blair's
over you and your flat chest.
She didn't have to trick me to
make me pick her instead of you.
Now that you mention it,
that witch does have a really
nice body, doesn't she?
[whack]
[Death] It would be best if you
just shut up for a while.
[Maka]
You men.
All of you. You're horrible...
Cheating on every woman!
But you... You I actually
decided to trust.
I put my faith in you.
[Maka]
I can't believe this.
I wish that all of
you would just die!
Hey Soul...You said that all
women make wild assumptions
without reasoning
first, right...?
That's what you said?
Well, what reason do
men have for cheating...?!
It's not fair...
How am I supposed
to know? I can't answer that.
After all, cool men don't
cheat on their
partners, do they?
Maka!
We've got them all...
Good job.
[Maka thinking] Yes,
Soul...Thank you for that.
In the end, the shape and form
don't matter at all...
It's only the soul
that matters, right...?
Nothing else.
[Maka]
Once you eat that...
That's right... With this soul
I'll become a Death Scythe.
[Soul cries out]
The power...!
I can feel incredible power!
[Soul]
Or not.
[Soul burps]
No way.
Meow.
[Maka]
Don't tell me...
You're not really...
I never said that I
was a witch, did I?
You just made that
assumption all on your own.
I'm really just a cat with a
ridiculous amount
of magical power.
Huh?!
The shape and form don't
matter, isn't that right...?
Huh, Soul?
[Death]
Yes... Just as I suspected.
The cat'll do...
Yes, Blair...
I'll be your cat toy any day--
[whack]
[Soul] You've
gotta be kidding me...!
Does this mean
I ate 99 human souls
and one cat soul?!
That just cannot be right!
And that's not all.
[Death] The witch's soul
is very important...
If you slip up,
all of the ninety-nine
Kishin souls
the two of you have collected
so far will be confiscated.
All of them will be confiscated.
All... confiscated.
[Maka]
So that means...
We failed?!
[Soul] Damn it...
damn it... damn it.
We have to start all over.
As the meister,
I'll take responsibility okay?
Aw, man! And I was this
close to being the coolest
guy in the academy!
He just ate your soul,
you damn cat.
What are you
still doing up there?!
You aren't very smart,
are you little girlie?
Don't you know that
all cats have nine souls?
So, Soul...
When are you gonna leave
this dumb girl for me anyway?
Blair go away...!
Stop following us, will ya?!
[Blair] Come on Soul...
you know you want to.
This situation
isn't cool at all.
[Narrator] The boy's name...
...is Black Star...
He is an assassin...
...shrouded in darkness.
With his partner,
he stalks his enemies
from the shadows.
[Black Star] Tsubaki... the head
of the table... he's the target?
[Tsubaki] Yes... We're
after Alcapone
along with his associates...
About a hundred souls in all.
[Black Star]
A hundred versus me...
What I like.
[Tsubaki]
Black Star...
Those are Kishin souls
down there-- ones who have
strayed out onto
the path of evil...
We have to reclaim them all.
[Narrator] Black Star...
He is the meister
who controls Tsubaki,
the magic Dark Arm...
But this powerful young
boy still has much to learn.
Let's go.
[Narrator]
Prologue Two...
Black Star... Coming soon...
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka]
And that's it...
That's the beginning
of Soul Eater...
I hope everyone liked it.
[Soul]
It wasn't cool.
[Maka] All right, Soul, when are
you gonna stop sulking?
[Soul] Fine... So, in the next
episode, you get to hear all
about an arrogant assassin and
his fights against a mob boss
and a samurai.
[Maka] Good. But we're not
gonna tell you any more.
It's not dinner time yet.
This is just a snack.
[Soul] What good
is a little snack?
[Maka] Well... it's tasty,
for one thing.
[Soul] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
"I am the Star! ~The Big Man
is Showing Up Here?~"
[Maka] Watch it,
or I'll take your soul!