A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
Tsubaki...!
Enchanted Sword Mode!
Right!
♪ opening song ♪
Uh, Kid...
What're we doing flying into the
middle of nowhere like this?
It's not like it was
my decision...
And I would really rather
not talk about it, okay?
Yeah, fine, but do you think
you could at least give us an
idea of where we're going?
Yeah...
that's fair enough.
We're going to a place
called Sarcophagus.
Sarcophagus?
That's right...
And it's aptly named, too.
And why's that?
It used to be just an ordinary
old village like any other.
But that was twenty years ago.
Things have changed.
Changed how?
Well...
One day...
It's citizens suddenly
disappeared...
Every last one of them.
What?
How could all those people
vanish into thin air?
To this day, no one knows.
The people sent to
investigate vanished,
just like the village's
citizens-- gone without a trace.
After awhile...
The investigation was given up.
It would have been
too dangerous to continue...
The entire area was locked down
to prevent further
disappearances...
That's where we're going.
There it is.
That's Sarcophagus.
The Last Magic Toolo~ Mission
Impossible for Unarmed Kid?
See that?
That wall was hastily built...
Almost like the builders
were desperately
trying to cover something
up before anyone saw it.
Like the academy's doing now.
This place is givin'
me the creeps.
Maybe we should forget
the mission, huh?.
I hope we see a monster!
Don't say stuff like that!
Are you crazy?!
No, no, no!
Not happening.
I am not going in there.
You know I can't deal
with creepy stuff...!
I've even got a
doctor's note that
specifically says
to avoid monsters.
You want to see it?
I'll show it to you!
You can calm down...
I'm not taking the
two of you with me.
Seriously?
We don't know what caused
the disappearances...
It could be a monster...
...or a virus...
...or maybe even some kind
of chemical weapon...
...but one thing we
do know for sure...
...no human who's
ever gone in there
has made it back out alive.
I can't risk taking you
guys in there with me...
...not when I have no idea
what we'd be up against...
It would simply
be too dangerous.
Much as I hate to admit it,
you've got a point there.
I'm guessing that's why
Dad sent me instead
of one of the other meisters.
My Reaper body is less
vulnerable than most.
Even so, this is
still dangerous.
Yes, but what
does that matter...?
My dad has made his
policies on this clear...
Our top priority
is the Magic Tools.
That's what you're after here?
If I'm not out in forty minutes,
head back for the academy.
Go straight there...
You will not come in after me.
Instead of sending me out
to help battle the Kishin,
Dad gives me this mission...
Well, soon enough
I'll see what's
so important about this Tool.
We've lost contact with
the thirteenth squadron...
Fifteen and seventeen:
circle around and
attack the enemy in
area thirty-four!
It sounds like it's
complete chaos out there.
All in all, I'd say it
could be going better.
Maybe it's time for us to
assume the command.
And what're we supposed to say?
What orders do we
give that'll help them?
I don't know, but anything
would be better than
standing here doing
nothing while they fight.
That's where you've
got it wrong.
If we start giving
random orders,
we could stir up even
more confusion.
No, not the scary face again.
Listen to you two...
Sometimes I envy your freedom.
You can go wherever you want,
do whatever you want,
whenever you want...
You can take real action.
You aren't chained here.
Know what I mean?
He's got a point.
At least we can leave.
I guess we're not the only
ones who're frustrated.
If his soul wasn't
bound to Death City,
Lord Death would
have been the first
one on that battlefield
fighting the Kishin.
Here we are...
The vanishing village.
So far I don't sense
anything abnormal about
this place other than
its emptiness...
It's utterly silent.
But still, there has
to be something here.
What's that?
Where the hell am I?
This looks like the inside
of some sort of ancient ruin.
Hey...!
Hey, boss man!
I'm not your boss man...
Please, just call me Joe.
Boss, come here...!
We've got lunch all ready.
It's time to eat!
I don't care what you say,
I'm still not your boss.
Mister Boss Man...
There's coffee down
here for you, too!
Boss or not, I can
still have a cup of coffee.
The coffee?
Here...
Have some!
Yum-my, yum-my coffee!
This is the coffee?
This is the tool?
Looks like a key.
The biggest key
that I've ever seen.
This seems too easy...
I just waltz into a deserted
city, grab the Magic Tool,
and walk back out again?
Maybe it's a fake...
If so, it's a good one...
It looks authentic
enough to me, anyway.
Hold on...!
Slow down...!
Maka!
Do you hear me...?
Stop running!
I know you want to move fast...
But where are you going?
I don't know.
Nice one.
Probably should have figured out
where we were going first...
I know you want to
find Medusa and Crona...
...but you won't do it
running around blindly.
You are familiar with the whole
'look before you
leap' thing, right?
Yeah...
I know you're right...
Sorry.
So...
what do you wanna do now?
Well...
I can try using my
soul perception...
...that should sniff out Medusa.
That won't do any good if
she has her Soul Protect on.
True, but there's still
Professor Stein...
...and Crona and
Miss Marie are out
there hunting the witch too...
If I can find any of their
souls, they'll lead me to her.
Lovely.
So now we've got
Professor Stein,
who even Lord Death
couldn't locate...
...and then there's Miss Marie
and Crona, who went after him...
We're trying to find three
people who could be anywhere in
the world and we don't have a
clue where to start looking...
Oh, yeah, I'm sure that's
going to work out perfectly.
Don't be so negative, Soul.
I know it's going to work.
Of course...
I'll still need your help.
Uh...
sure thing.
Damn it!
I guess this is the security
system guarding the tool.
Are you qualified?
Do you have what it takes
to wield the Magic Tool?
Creepy clown...
Who are you?
What are you doing here...?
Were you the one
who destroyed the village?
Answer me!
What am I doing here?
I prevent meddlesome humans
from entering this place...
...or from leaving
it alive, at least.
I destroy anyone who
touches the Magic Tool.
You're responsible for what
happened twenty years ago!
That is correct...
I protect the resting place
of the last Magic Tool.
You killed them all
because of the tool?
Those foolish humans...
They dug up this ruin
twenty years ago
and discovered the tool...
They weren't qualified
to wield it either...
So I ate them...
I ate them all.
They were delicious.
All trespassers must die...
That includes you, too.
Snack time!
You won't make a
meal of me that easily.
Running, are you...?
I won't let you get far.
With a huge body like that,
he'll never be able to
squeeze in after me.
What a poorly designed
security system.
Aw, are you stuck?
Not good!
Close one.
But I did it.
Now I just have to make
it back to Liz and Patty.
What's that?!
There're two?!
Didn't see that coming.
Chow time.
Oink! Oink! Oink...!
Oink! Oink! Oink!
Kid sure is taking
his time, huh?
There's no reason to worry.
It might take a while,
but I'm sure everything'll
be hunky-dory...
If anyone can do it,
it's our meister.
Do it, Kid!
I believe in you!
But just to be safe...
...maybe we should go in
there and check up on him.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What,
are you kidding me?!
We'd be nuts to go into
someplace as creepy as that!
Do you have a death
wish or something?!
It'll be fine.
I say we go in after him.
Seriously...?
Were you listening
to a thing I just said?
Of course I was...
You said something
about a pig, right?
Don't...
...you...
...ever...
Listen when I talk?!
What's that?
What's what?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I didn't hear anything.
Nothing at all!
Still coming.
Perfect symmetry!
No symmetry!
Not symmetrical at all.
Now perfectly symmetrical.
Now not symmetrical at all.
What a perfect pose!
Unbelievable beauty...
The very definition
of symmetry...
Oh dear.
Oh, the destructive
power of true beauty!
A little further.
Just to that building.
Give it back...
Hand over the Magic Tool now!
Hiya Kid, how are ya?
We just came to check on you!
You came after me?
Sure...
...what else would we do?
Not so scared of
creepy monsters anymore?
Now, Patty!
Okay...!
On it!
You had no right
to destroy this village...
You're going to pay for that.
Are you ready
for your punishment?
Hand it over.
Hand it over NOW!!
These guys aren't easy.
This is bad, Kid.
Our shots won't go through.
What now?
Resonance stable.
Noise: two point seven percent.
Black needles are fully
charged with soul wavelength.
Feedback ready...
In five seconds.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Ready to fire.
Symmetry...
At least your end
will be beautiful.
Death Cannon!
Mission accomplished.
Unable to activate
auto-recovery...
System down...
Not responding...
Estimated damage received:
ninety-two percent...
Activation time remaining:
three minutes.
It moved...?! What now?
You who defeated
this guardian...
Hear me now.
It's different from
the voice before...
What's going on?
This is a warning.
Before you proceed...
Make certain you have
the will to use
the Magic Tool you now possess.
For those who
are not qualified...
...there will be no glory...
Only destruction awaits.
Maybe he's right.
How can we know for certain
that the course we follow is
better than the one our
enemies have chosen...?
Who can promise that the
academy will never use
the Magic Tools
with evil intent?
So that's it...?
The thing we
were sent here to find?
Yes...
And given the level of
security set up around it,
I'd say my dad's not the only
one who thinks it's important.
Kay...
...so what's he
planning to use it for?
That I don't know yet.
If I did know...
...things would be much simpler.
What that robot thing said...
...is it still bothering you?
Yeah, it is.
Because of that...
I'm not sure if
handing this over to
my dad is the right
thing to do.
This is a warning.
For those who
are not qualified...
...there will be no glory...
Only destruction awaits.
Ya-hoo!
Well then.
Looks like it's just you and me.
♪ closing music ♪
Despite the dangers
that lie ahead,
they continue on their path...
The woman who would
recover her lost partner...
...and the boy who would
confront his devious mother...
A mismatched pair struggling
toward an unknown fate...
What will await them at the
end of their journey...?
Will they find hope?
Or only more despair...?
Hey, who is that?
It's Patty, silly!
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Weakling Crona's
Determination...
For You, For Always
Being By My Side?
Patty's here!