[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[footsteps]
[knock on door]
[heavy door creaking open]
[Maka]
Hey, Crona! Good morning!
Oh...
G...Good morning.
Come on, let's get going.
♪ opening song ♪
[Marie]
Open up your books...
Let's take a look at chart
one on page one-oh-eight.
We covered this
briefly yesterday,
but now let's take
a closer look...
As I mentioned, soul study is
divided into several
different fields...
[Crona thinks]
I wonder...
You know, I'm really happy
to have you here, Crona.
[Crona]
Yeah.
[Maka] Come on Crona.
Quit hiding...
There's nothing to
be afraid of here.
[Crona thinks]
Why...
Why is everybody
so nice to me?
Why do they go out
of their way to help me?
Why...
Good pass!
Good blocking, Crona!
Good job, Crona.
You can do it.
Take it away from him!
Come on Crona!
You can do it! Take it!
Looks like things are
starting to get better for him.
Yeah... it's slow going,
but we're working on it.
So, Soul.
How have you been doing?
Huh?
That wound
you took in the chest.
Aw it's fine...
Anyway, dwelling too much
on the past ain't cool...
Especially when it comes
to a fight we ended up losing.
You can just forget like that?
Maka's been working
hard with Crona...
I don't want to spoil that
by dredging up
any bad memories.
I get it.
All right!
Let's get in on this.
[Soul]
Gimme that a sec.
Your center of
gravity is high, see?
You need to bend
your knees a little more...
relax your shoulders,
and then throw...
Here. You give it a try.
I think it's time
for another party.
[Maka]
Drying Happiness...!
o~Whose Tears Sparkle
in the Moonlight?o~
[swanky jazz music]
Hey, Soul... thanks for
contributing to
the music selection.
Sure... Is this one gonna
be okay, though...?
You said to bring
something catchy...
...so I decided
on this punk record.
But it might not work
that well for this crowd.
Yeah...
Well, then... play the piano!
There's one right there.
[Soul]
Why the sudden craving?
It's been awhile
since I've heard you.
I think I'll pass on that one.
I gotta take a leak.
Aw, he got away.
I had no idea he
could play the piano.
Yeah, he's only played
for me once, though...
...right before we
first became partners.
What kind of song?
It's hard to explain.
Something dark and strange.
He said, "This is
the kinda person I am,"
and just started playing.
Something about that song
and the way he played it
must've gotten to me...
...and we became partners.
Well I'm sorry I missed it.
Tsubaki...! Seconds.
Get me seconds!
Yeah, okay.
Sorry, Crona...
A noisy group like this
must make you uncomfortable.
I'm not completely
used to it yet.
But... I'm not feeling
uncomfortable either.
No one's going
anywhere for a bit...
So you can take your time.
Join the group at your own pace.
There's no need to
rush this sort of thing.
Yo...! What're you hanging
out over here for...?
It's a party!
Let's have some fun!
What was that for?
Don't bully Crona!
What's up!...?
Someone's bullying Crona?
Crona...!
If someone's giving
you a hard time,
you just let ol'
Black Star know.
I'll throw 'im out
the nearest window!
Why is everyone...
...so nice...
to someone like me?
It's simple, Crona...
That's just what friends do.
If you're a friend,
then feed me!
Here... Tsubaki made it herself.
I sure hope you enjoy it!
Gross.
[Black Star] Crona, come and
hang out at my place next time.
[Tsubaki]
I don't mind cooking.
It's worth it for
someone with an
appetite as big
as Ragnarok's is.
[Maka]
See you later, then.
Bye, bye!
I'll see you tomorrow.
[dogs barking and howling]
[Ragnarok]
Hey, Crona!
You should try to find
a partner who can
cook like that Tsubaki girl.
How can I do that?
I thought you were
already my partner.
[Crona] The party was a
lot of fun, wasn't it?
[Ragnarok] The food
was good, at least.
I've been waiting
for you... Hi, Crona.
Lady Medusa!
Very good, Crona...
I wasn't sure you'd recognize
me in this sad state...
Embarrassing, isn't it?
[Ragnarok] You've gotten
all tiny, just like me.
Wh... why... why are
you back in Death City?
[Medusa]
I came for you, Crona.
I've been so
worried about you.
You're worried...
Does that mean you're here
to bring me back with you?
Oh, no... You should
stay in the academy...
...and continue your
work as my spy.
[Crona] Huh...?! what are
you talking about...?
A spy...? Me?
There's no need to
be so modest about it...
That's why you infiltrated
the DWMA, right?
To become a spy?
[Medusa]
You did a good job,
but now I have a task
only you can do...
There's a secret vault
somewhere within the academy...
For now, all I need
you to do is find it.
I'm counting on you... Crona.
No, wait, I... I've made
some friends at the academy...
Doing this might make
them angry at me.
But you'll do it, won't you...?
For your dear mother?
Yes, ma'am. I understand.
(goobeebee) Things are
getting interesting!
Death City is growing
thick with madness.
It won't be long before
something happens.
Folk music? Gross!
You're joking, right?
Tell me you're joking.
I didn't ask for your opinion!
[Liz]
Seriously, though?
How can you listen to that?
[Patty]
Folk music is stupid!
I may not do
very well on tests...
...but even I know
that much dude.
[Maka] I listen to
whatever I want!
Leave me alone!
Crona?
(oh) Sorry...
Um... I think I'll...
...head back to my room now.
[Maka]
See you tomorrow!
[Black Star]
See ya!
What's wrong with him...?
He's been more withdrawn
than usual lately.
Really...? How can you
tell the difference?
You'd better get moving...
...or Medusa won't be happy!
Hi, hi...! Good to
see ya, Justin...!
How're things?
[rap music blasting in his ears]
Hey, Spirit, give me a hand...
Justin's got his headphones
in as usual, and he can't read
my lips with this mask on...
Do me a favor and repeat
everything I say for the
rest of the conversation, cool?
What am I some
kind of parrot now...?!
Can't he just take
out the headphones?
[Death] Okay...
now repeat after me.
Justin... I called you into
the Death Room today
because I need to explain the
new assignment I'm giving you.
Hey... hold on!
These are your orders
from Lord Death... Listen up...
The reason you were
called in here today...
...is to receive your
latest assignment.
Okay... What is it?
[Death] This is a very
important mission.
This is a very
[Death] You're aware that,
because of her extraordinary
scouting abilities,
Azusa has been
given the task of
hunting down the Kishin?
You know Azusa's the one
in charge of hunting
down the Kishin, right?
But there's a limit to
what she can do from here.
That's why I need you to help...
While she's using her eyes,
I want you to use your legs...
Travel everywhere,
searching for the Kishin.
But she can only do
so much with her eyes.
That's where you come in.
You're gonna be her legs.
[Death] Hey,
that's not what I said!
Repeat it properly
from now on.
You're taking too
long to explain it.
[Death]
Say that again.
Yeah, fine, I got it.
[Death]
Now then...
Here's what I'm
hoping will happen.
If you can make enough
noise during your search...
...you may be able to flush out
the cowardly Kishin from
wherever it's hiding...
Do you understand
the assignment?
[Death Scythe imitating Death]
Here's what I'm hoping
will happen.
If you can make enough
noise during your search...
...you may be able to
flush out the cowardly
Kishin from
wherever it's hiding...
Do you understand
the assignment?
Oh, what a truly
wondrous assignment...!
I accept the mission
with great pleasure!
[Death]
I'm counting on you to succeed.
[Justin]
Right!
[Ragnarok] Looks like the
hallway's off limits from here.
(goobeebee)
Which might mean it's a good
place to look for the vault.
[Crona] What if somebody sees
me wandering down here?
What am I supposed to do then?
[Ragnarok] It's not my problem
if you get yourself caught.
[Marie]
Hello...? Who's there?
Oh, it's you, Crona...
What are you doing?
You shouldn't be
down here, you know.
This area's off limits.
Um... I, uh... well I...
[Ragnarok]
You saved us, Marie...!
We were trying to find our
room, and we lost our way!
Well, I'm actually a
little lost myself...
The academy's layout
is confusing.
I still don't understand it.
But we'll figure
it out somehow.
Just leave it to me!
Don't worry.
I'll help you find your room.
Now let's see here...
It's this way!
[Ragnarok]
You sure about that?
[everyone breathing heavy]
[Marie]
Well we made it!
[Ragnarok]
Thanks a lot.
We couldn't have
done it without you.
If you run into any
more difficulties,
don't hesitate to let
me know, okay?
I'll be glad to help...
...except with directions.
I'll leave you here,
then. Good night!
[Crona] Um. The teacher's
office is that way.
[Eruka]
Ribbit.
I hate this...
I can't stand going
back and forth from
such a dangerous place.
[Crona]
Eruka...
[Eruka]
What's your progress...?
Do you know where
the secret vault is?
I can't do this...
I can't deal with
this kind of situation.
That isn't what we
wanted to hear, Crona...
Right, Lady Medusa?
It's okay...
You're doing very well, Crona.
How about this...
I'll give you a different
mission instead.
Tell me how professor
Stein's been doing.
[Crona] I don't see
him very often,
so I'm not sure how much
I can tell you about him.
From what I can tell,
he's started partnering
with Miss Marie...
And they're living together now.
[Medusa]
Marie...?
What's she like?
She's gentle and kind...
She's friendly to everybody,
and she always looks out for me.
[Medusa]
(hmm)... Is that so?
All right...
Let's make use of that
sweet nature of hers.
Have a good day, Miss Marie!
You too! See you tomorrow.
[Crona]
Miss Marie.
Yes...?
Is something wrong, Crona?
Um... it's just that...
Can I help you
with something?
Well, yes...
Actually...I...
There's something
I wanted to talk to you--
Goodbye, Miss Marie!
Oh, have a good
afternoon, girls.
I have an idea...
Why don't you
come to my house...?
We can talk over some tea.
Oh... okay.
[Medusa] There's a
tiny listening device
hidden inside the pen.
All you have to do is
place it in Professor
Stein's laboratory.
[Marie]
Here you go.
This place didn't have
anything but beakers
and test tubes
when I got here...
I had to bring the
cups in myself.
These are very nice cups.
[Ragnarok] Who cares as long
as you can drink from it?
It looks like you
have added your own
girly touch here and there.
[Marie] I can't bring in
too much stuff,
or Stein will throw a fit.
But I'm adjusting,
little by little...
So, tell me what it is
that's been troubling you?
Oh...! You see... I, uh...
Hey! Why didn't I get any?
I'm thirsty too!
Huh...? Ragnarok can drink...?
But he doesn't
have a mouth, does he?
Sure I do...
You wanna see?
So sorry...
I'll make some for you now.
[Ragnarok] There's
no need to hurry.
Crona...! Now's your chance!
[Crona]
Yeah. Right.
What are you
waiting for, you moron?
Do you take sugar?
[Ragnarok] H...
How about some pepper?
I like it spicy.
Oh, okay... Whatever you say.
[Marie]
Sorry for the wait.
Now, then... let's pick up
where we left off, shall we...?
You were getting ready to
tell me something,
weren't you Crona.
What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Okay, if you're sure.
So, Crona... you wanted to talk?
Thank you, but...
I'm much...
...much more r-r-r-relaxed now.
Really?
Well, I don't know
what was wrong,
but I'm glad
you're feeling better.
It's getting late...
I should be going home.
[Marie]
Oh, stop by any time.
(goobeebee)
That went smoothly.
Hold on a second, Crona.
Wha...wha...wha...
What is it? Is something wrong?
Your pen. You almost forgot it.
Here.
Goodbye...!
See ya!
Be careful on your
way back home!
[Eruka]
How'd it go?
Did you do it?
[Stein]
I'm home.
[Marie]
Welcome back, Stein.
[Eruka]
Ribbit.
You hear that?
We've got 'em...
I'm impressed.
How were you able
to get Marie to drink it?
It was easy.
While she was out of the room,
we just added a
little drop to her tea.
[Eruka] The magical snake
Marie drank contained
more than a listening device.
It will also speed up
the spread of Stein's
madness when he's near her.
[Marie] Crona
dropped by just now.
[Stein] Oh...?
Is something wrong?
[Marie]
He doesn't seem to be
used to life at
the academy yet,
and I can tell
it's bothering him...
But he's a good kid...
...so sweet and quiet.
Not even suspicious...
What an idiot.
[Marie]
I'm sure he'll be fine...
He'll adjust to this
new life at his own pace.
Crona and all the other students
are what make teaching
at the academy worthwhile.
[Crona]
It's getting late...
I'm going back to my room now.
[Eruka]
Oh... Crona?
Medusa will be proud
of you for doing so well.
[Crona softly sobs]
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka singing]
Excalibur! Excalibur!
From the United K...
I'm looking for heaven...
I'm going to California!
Excalibur! Excalibur!
From the United K...
I'm looking for heaven...
--I'm going to California!
[Soul] On the next episode
of Soul Eater:
[Soul] The Legend
of the Holy Sword 3:
The Academy Gang Leader's Tale?
[Soul]
How lame!
[Maka]
Excalibur!