[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Justin] It's been
many years since
the last time I set
foot on this ground.
Oh, great lord... Please...
Grant the people comfortable
lives and dignified deaths.
♪ opening song ♪
Crona...
It's okay, really...
I promise you.
I wonder how
he's doing now.
Aw, man.
[Sid]
About the Demon Sword...
[Death]
Hmm?
He surrendered to us after
the battle under the school,
so we've taken
him into custody...
...but I think you should be
the one to decide how he's
dealt with now
that we have him.
[Death]
Yes, I should...
Is there something
bothering you, sir?
[Death] Yes...
There's something...
...strange about
the Demon Sword.
What do you mean, by 'strange'?
[Death] The Demon
Sword has devoured
a great number of
human souls, right...?
So we'd expect him to be well
on his way to becoming a Kishin.
But nothing could be
further from the truth.
[Sid]
What do you mean?
[Death] I don't know how
it's even possible...
...but I guess you could say
it seems like something
has had a sort of...
...purifying effect
on him recently.
What do you think about it, Sid?
I don't have
the slightest idea...
But I do think we need
to hold the Demon Sword
accountable for all the
horrible things he's done.
I realize he's a child
and he was led by a witch,
but we can't ignore his actions.
I think the same
severe punishment
that we always use for cases
like this should
apply here as well.
Don't you agree?
[Death]
Hmmm...
[Sid]
Hmm...?
[Death] Dunno...
so I think I'm gonna put it off.
[Maka] The Death
Scythes Convene...
Stop Dad's Staff
Reassignment!!?
[Maka]
Hey! What're you doing?
Just come on.
I'm not coming anywhere...
Lord Death specifically told us
to stay put until our
injuries are all healed.
Seriously...
If ya stay put any longer
than you already have...
Look...
You'll start sprouting
mushrooms,
and that's not cool.
[Maka]
I will not.
Oh come on.
You know you want to.
What are you planning, Soul?
Just a little change of pace.
Huh?
[Black Star]
Yo!
[Death]
On to the next issue...
Including Spirit,
what's our head count looking
like so far for the gathering
of the eight Death Scythes?
[Sid]
Well...
It appears that Justin
has now arrived...
Counting Spirit and the other
two that got in earlier,
we have a total of four.
[Death] Okay, we've got
half of them at least...
What're the other four up to?
It looks like the ones in
charge of Europe and West Asia
are too busy with work and
can't make it here right now.
[Death]
That's no good...
What about the one we've
got stationed down
in South America?
It's kinda hard to tell with
all the growling and barking.
And Africa?
Yeah, they won't take our calls.
[Death] Well... I guess
four of 'em is just gonna
have to be good enough...
Here's hoping.
[Marie]
Ugh. No, no, no.
[Yumi]
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me...?
This is not where I
should be right now,
that's what's wrong.
There are more important
things I need to be doing.
[Yumi]
Don't be ridiculous...
There's a Kishin out
walking the earth again...
What could possibly be more
important than dealing with it?
You're still young.
I wouldn't expect
you to understand.
All I want to do is retire
and find myself a
good husband,
but I still get all this
work dumped on me...
Doesn't that seem unfair?!
When there's work to be done,
we don't have a choice.
I devote myself completely
to every man I date,
but they always
end up dumping me.
Have you ever thought that
maybe your devotion puts so
much pressure on them that
they feel the need to
run away from you?
[Marie] You don't understand
the power of love!
Yeah, maybe you're
right about that...
but you don't understand
the power of your punches.
[Marie]
Oh... sorry.
Anyway... it's old
fashioned to think that only
marriage can make
a woman happy.
Okay, Marie, what is it now?
[Marie]
I've decided...
I'm going to marry this toilet.
That's it! It'll be perfect...!
After all, what's more
accepting than a toilet?
It'll take anything
and everything!
It's an ideal husband!
Hold on a second.
Let's just think this over.
Wouldn't it be annoying when
the toilet seat was left up?
I can live with that.
It's not a big deal.
[Yumi]
Oh no...!
I've got to stop her!
Uh... Okay,
but nobody's perfect.
Even the toilet might complain
a bit if you put more pressure
on it than it can take.
And I hate to tell you this,
but he could secretly spring
a leak without you knowing.
[Marie]
A leak...? How indecent.
It's over...
You dirty cheater!
[Marie] Okay...!
We can go see Lord Death now.
And Marie the
Pulverizer strikes again.
She won't be
retiring any time soon.
[Death Scythe]
Need something?
[Stein] Yes... We need to go and
check in with Lord Death.
Nope. I'm not goin'. Sorry.
And why's that?
[Death Scythe]
Tell me this, Stein...
Why do you think Lord Death
is gathering all the other
Death Scythes here at the DWMA?
Because the Kishin's revived
and we need to come up
with a plan quickly before it
can do any more damage.
No, you're wrong...
Lord Death's totally
planning to send me away...
Transferred and demoted.
Oh... yeah?
I mean, think about it!
If I'd only stayed with
him like I'm supposed to,
he woulda been able
to use me to defeat Asura.
[Stein] So now you're
polishing sconces
to earn some points with him?
That a problem?
[Stein]
Wow, you are dumb.
Yeah, well, I'm a little
desperate here, Stein...
I don't want my ex-wife
to take full custody of Maka...
If that happens, I won't
ever get to see my little girl,
and then it'll hardly even
feel like I'm
her father anymore.
It already hardly
seems like you are.
You're actually desperate
enough to roll up your sleeves
and do some hard labor.
That's right! And I'll roll 'em
up even more if I have to.
Look over there.
It's Stein, your first love.
[Marie] I don't know what
you're talking about.
Hey...! Long time no see.
Hello you two.
It's her.
[Death Scythe and Stein]
Queen of Committee Chairmen
You were always an annoying,
bossy brat, Azusa.
Yes, I remember you complaining
every time I tried to
dismember a passer-by.
I'm with her on that.
[Yumi] Wouldn't you say the
Kishin's revival was largely
a result of your
blundering ineptitude?
Hey, now! Let's not go sayin'
stuff like that when we're
in front of Lord Death, okay?
[Yumi] I don't know if
that'll be possible...
I have a tendency to
speak my mind at all times.
Come to think of it, Marie...
Weren't you planning to retire
right after you became
a Death Scythe?
Please don't remind me.
All right...! There will
be no more talking.
Lord Death is waiting
for us in the Death Room.
Everyone line up!
At attention!
[Death Scythe and Stein]
Here we go again.
[Justin]
Oh!
Great Lord...!
Why will you not speak
your magnificent words that
I may hear them
and swiftly obey?
[Death]
Uhh...
Ooohhh...! This is a tragedy!
I am unable to hear your voice.
[Death] Umm...
actually, you should--
Take out the ear phones!
Huh?
It's good to
see you all again...
Justin, at your
service as always.
[Death] Thank you for coming
all this way, Death Scythes.
Now, then, let's get
down to business...
I assume you already know
why I've called you to the
DWMA on such short notice.
Please no transfer...!
Please no transfer!
[Death]
The Kishin Asura,
a former member of my
personal guard, has revived.
Obviously,
we need to discuss this.
Despite Asura's
incredible strength,
he's still a
big old scardey cat...
I doubt he will make
any moves this early on.
This means the most pressing
task for us at the moment
is not determining how
to counteract Asura's actions,
but establishing a strategy for
dealing with his
madness wavelengths.
That's the real danger now.
Stein, could you answer any
questions the others may
have about these wavelengths?
Yes.
What are they, exactly...?
Can we consider them comparable
to the soul wavelengths
of the Kishin?
Yes... but these wavelengths
are on a godly level.
What makes the
wavelengths so dangerous?
What can they do?
[Stein] Everyone in
the world possesses
at least a small
amount of madness.
I am no exception.
Asura's madness wavelengths
rouse the insanity that
sleeps deep in people's souls,
magnifying it.
The madness
spreads like a disease.
I could feel the waves of it
the moment Asura was revived.
[Stein insanely laughs]
A plague of madness.
And you're saying anybody
can feel its effects?
Not quite.
It might be relatively difficult
for a person like Justin
to be infected by the madness.
Also... for the time being,
at least, I think the
outbreak will be limited...
I doubt it will have
much effect on ordinary
people as they go
about their daily business.
Then, what major problem
does the madness pose initially?
[Yumi] It will
strengthen the wicked.
[Stein]
That's correct...
For example, dismembering living
things has always
intrigued me...
The madness enhances that.
[Death]
And?
[Stein]
There's much more...
The wavelengths will
awaken witches
who are now dormant...
...and they will affect
more than just people...
Natural disasters,
unusual weather phenomena...
All sorts of horrors
are possible.
Enemies who have been
inactive for a long time
will begin moving.
The reason we're
in this situation...
...is the blundering
of these two idiots.
[Yumi] Lord Death, have you
given any thought as to what
should be done with them?
[Death]
Yes... about that...
[Death Scythe]
No transfer!
Anything but
reassignment, please!
[Death] I'm thinking a very
slight staff reassignment
might be in order.
[Death Scythe]
What?! No!
My happy life
with my daughter.
It's gone...! Gone for good...!
What future can I
ever have now...?
How am I gonna
explain this to Maka...?
I don't wanna see the sad
look on her dear little face!
[Death]
No, no... Calm down, Spirit...
You're still going to
be my personal weapon.
Are you really
going to keep me?!
[Death] You shouldn't
be so surprised...!
You are the only Death Scythe
who is actually
a Death Scythe...
Have a little more
confidence in yourself.
Oh, Lord...! You are truly
a kind and benevolent ruler.
Recently I've sent you off
to serve as Stein's temporary
weapon whenever
he needed you...
That has to change...
You must avoid leaving
the academy as much as
physically possible from now on.
Understood, sir!
[Death]
One other change...
I think we should have
an additional Death Scythe
stationed here to help
fortify the DWMA's defenses.
Marie... I'm assigning
that duty to you...
I'd like you to be
Stein's new partner.
Huh...? Why me?
Oh no!
Please, you can't be serious...!
I've completely lost the
motivation to work...!
I even chose to be in
charge of Oceania because
I knew it would be
peaceful and easy...
If I'm always busy here
at the academy it'll take me
even longer to find a husband!
[Stein]
It's okay...
I have a feeling your obsessive
tendencies will come in handy.
[Marie]
Don't say that.
Lord Death, sir...
What task would
you like me to take?
[Death]
You'll use your wide field
of vision to locate Asura...
...wherever he's run off to.
You'll also be in charge
of Oceania while Marie is
stationed here at the school.
Right.
[Death]
And as for your task, Justin.
Uh, Justin?
Well, never mind Justin for now!
Obviously, life here at the
DWMA is going to have
to change in the coming weeks...
We're entering a difficult time,
but at least it'll be exciting!
Okay! Class dismissed.
[Death]
Oh, hang back a second, Spirit.
[Death Scythe]
Yes, sir?
[Death] There's something
you and I need to discuss...
...in private.
[Black Star] All right!
Let's play some basketball!
Yeah!
Hey, Maka!
Get over here!
Why should I...?
You said you were fine
with me reading a
book on the sidelines.
That's the only reason
I agreed to come.
Well I lied. Sorry...
[Black Star]
It's not my fault, you know!
Liz suddenly flaked out on us,
so now we need you to play.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know how to play this.
Here...
...it's for your hair.
All right. Three on three.
These teams should
work for right now.
Hey, Kid...
Why couldn't Liz come
out and play today?
Something about nice nails
that took a long time to grow...
A regular game of
basketball would be boring...
Let's say the losing
captain gets a punishment.
That oughta make
things more interesting.
Yeah, sounds good...
What're the punishments?
[Soul] If we lose,
we'll move the picture frames
in Kid's place two centimeters.
[Kid]
Whoa whoa whoa!
That would be interesting.
All right. And if we lose,
then Captain Maka here
has to spend a whole day
hanging out with
her creepy old man.
Huh?!
Hold on!
That doesn't make any sense...!
Don't you wanna
be captain, Black Star?
You'll be the
center of attention!
It's so hard...!
But I feel really bad
for forcing you to play!
It'll be a sacrifice,
but I'll regretfully surrender
my captain duties to you, Maka.
You have to decide now
not to be an attention hog?
[Patty] You are wearing
the captain's cap, Maka.
Huh...?!
That's what you gave me?
Damn it...! I wanna be captain!
Fine with me.
Let's switch!
Okay, here we go.
Bring it on.
Huh?
Soul isn't on our team.
What's he doing
passing it to Black Star?
[Black Star]
Here.
Huh? Why'd Black
Star pass it back?
Right... let's do it.
Patty...! Captain Maka...
Zone defense, okay?
'Kay!
What's a zone...?
Somebody please tell me!
Now we're starting?
Stop you guys! Wait!
--Soul...! Pass! Pass!
--This is absolutely hopeless.
How am I supposed
to find a husband
in a place that's full of kids?
It'll be impossible!
Hey, nice shooting, Kid!
Are they students from the DWMA?
Yes... And they're your
students starting tomorrow.
That was a foul, Maka.
You can't double
dribble the ball.
Come on, you're the captain!
Shouldn't you know better?
Huh? I don't get it,
what's a double dribble?.
I mean it sounds kinda cool.
Oh-kay...
I don't have a boyfriend
right now, anyway.
I guess I might
as well do some work.
Oh, yeah, I forgot...
Everything's happened
so quickly.
I'll need to stay at
your place until
I can find an
apartment in town.
[Stein] That's fine,
but don't blame me if you
wind up dismembered.
[Marie] I have
complete faith in you.
[Death Scythe]
What is it, sir?
[Death]
Actually...
I need to talk to
you about Stein.
I'm pretty sure he's
realized it himself...
but his old madness is beginning
to take hold of him again.
[Death Scythe]
So you put him with Marie?
[Death] I think she's the best
partner for him right now.
Her soul wavelength
should have a positive
effect on the
madness inside him.
So, Spirit...
You're Stein's former partner...
Can I ask you to
keep an eye on his
situation for me as well?
[Death Scythe]
Yes.
Sheesh...
Is he always going to be
this much of a headache?
[Players shouting
out during game]
Hey.
Oh I didn't see
you there, Spirit.
What're they doing here...?
Didn't we tell 'em to stay
at home so they can heal?
I'm always amazed by
how carefree kids can be.
[Death Scythe]
I wouldn't call it carefree.
They just had the biggest
battle of their lives.
They're trying to regain
some normalcy in
their own way.
[Soul]
Game over...!
Final score: 20 to 4.
Maka's team loses.
--Pun...ish...ment...!
--I never even figured out
how to play the game!
Pun...ish...ment...!
Pun...ish...ment!
Whew...! Glad it's not me!
Maybe we should let
her off the hook.
I'm not so sure about that...
This doesn't seem much
more normal than
that fight underground...
It's still two sides
fighting for different goals.
Jeez, Stein...
A simple game like basketball,
and you still just can't
quite get it, can you?
Oh... Hey, what's
going on, Maka?
[Maka]
U-Umm...
...ya see... Papa...
Do... do you want
to hang out...
...like... Saturday?
[Death Scythe thinks] I never
thought this day would come!
To think, I almost
got sent away today!
[Maka in a dream] Hey, Papa!
Which do you want:
strawberry or banana?
Which shirt do you
think'll look better on me?
[Death Scythe]
It's cold out.
[Maka]
Thanks, Papa!
It's so nice and warm!
I... I thought Maka
was looking for normalcy!
Papa?
[Death Scythe vomits]
What's wrong, Papa...?
Are you okay?
Sorry...
It's just that I'm so happy!
Hang on!
I'll get some medicine for you!
No-- it's really--
I'm okay!
[Death Scythe thinks]
Shoot me now...
Happy puking...
I guess that's one more
thing I don't understand.
[Sid]
Lord Death...
You put it off before,
but I think we need to
decide what to do
with the Demon Sword.
[Death]
All right then...
I've made up my mind...
We'll enroll him in the academy!
Seriously?
[Death]
Yes, of course seriously.
Really... Not joking...
That's my decision.
The kid has some major
issues we'll have
to deal with, I know...
...but if we guide him
carefully enough,
he'll become an excellent
ally for the DWMA...
We could really use someone
like him on our side right now.
[Sid]
I understand...
But he's still in no condition
to enroll in classes.
[Death]
I agree with you...
That's why we'll move slowly...
His trial enrollment in the
academy begins tomorrow!
♪ closing song ♪
[Death Scythe]
It connects!
[Yumi] Yes... Finally,
all the seemingly
unrelated incidents
are connected.
[Death Scythe]
No, not that!
[Yumi] Do you mean
the link between
global warming and
human overuse of--
[Death Scythe]
No no no!
[Yumi]
Okay, what then...?
Are you doing a
connect-the-dots puzzle?
[Death Scythe]
Please! Come on!
[Yumi]
Then maybe--
[Death Scythe] If you'll shut up
for a second, I'll say it!
[Both] The hip bone's
connected to the leg bone!
[Death Scythe]
Umm... Azusa?
[Yumi] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Exciting an Embarrassing
Trial Enrollment!
The DWMA New Lifestyle
Support Fair is Open?
[Death Scythe]
You totally stole my thunder!