[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[dog panting]
[snake rattles]
[dog growls]
[dog yelps in pain]
I see a snake in the sky!
[Rachel's mom]
What are you doing, Rachel...?
Your father's waiting for us.
We need to get back home.
[Rachel]
Did you see it, Mommy?
The snake in the sky?
[Rachel's mom] I'm sure
it was just a cloud, dear.
That gray one is the one
I'm worried about.
We might get rain tonight.
[Rachel]
Which cloud, Mommy?
A puppy!
[Rachel's mom]
Wait!
It's probably dirty honey!
Leave it alone.
Hey, puppy, come here!
What's the matter...?
You're lonely, aren't you?
[snake rattle]
Rachel... sweetie...?
You shouldn't play
with stray dogs.
Listen to what Mommy said
and come away from there.
You don't want to
get in trouble, do you?
What is it, Rachel?
Nothing... Coming!
Sorry, Mommy.
♪ opening song ♪
[Sid] We brought back
the blueprints for the
Magic Tool as you asked us to.
After studying it,
we've determined it's
part of the Book of Eibon.
[Naigus]
Shall we dispose of it?
[Death]
No... Please see that the
plans are safely locked
up in the secret vault.
[Naigus] With something
as dangerous as this...
It's all right.
We'll take care of it.
[Death]
Sid... Naigus...
I'm sure it goes
without saying,
but not a word
of this to anyone...
Keep it between us...
Understood?
[TV girl repeats over and over]
An apple! An apple! An apple!
[Rachel's mom]
Rachel...
You've been watching
that for a long time.
Don't you think it's
about time to turn it off?
Always do what
your mother tells you...
If you're not a good girl,
you'll be punished.
[Rachel]
Good night, Mommy.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night, Rachel.
[Rachel's mom]
Don't you think Rachel's
been acting a
little, weird today?
[Rachel's dad]
'Weird' how?
[Rachel's mom]
I'm not sure how to explain it.
She just seemed kind of 'off'.
[Rachel's dad]
Kids are like that...
They change overnight
without their
parents noticing...
I don't think it's anything
you need to worry about.
She's just growing up,
that's all.
But...
You're right.
What...?! What happened?
[Rachel crying]
Mommy, Daddy, help!...
I saw a big, scary snake.
It was gonna swallow
me up and eat me...!
Make it stop!
A snake?
[Rachel's dad]
It's okay, sweetie...
It was just a bad dream.
There. You can sleep right
here next to Daddy, okay...?
Daddy's gonna make all those
mean snakes go away.
Isn't that right, Mommy?
Right!
[Maka]
Medusa's Revival...!
A Spider and Snake's
Fateful Reunion?
[Stein]
Quiet. Class is starting.
Is everybody in their seat?
You had us all worried
for a while there, Maka.
I'm glad the spell's gone
and you're back
to normal again.
Mm-hmm...
Feeling better than ever...
And ready for a good fight!
Oooh...! I bet we could
have a fight right now!
[Kid]
Sit down, Patty.
Fine but can we at
least have a party later?
[Liz] A party in
your honor, Maka.
We can invite
Crona too, if you'd like.
Yeah!
We'll all party together!
[Liz] We're missing someone
right now, though.
Let me guess...
Black Star's in yet
another fight, Tsubaki?
Uh-huh...
What a jerk. He goes off to
fight and leaves you here.
What's the deal with that guy?
It's how he is...
Black Star's a little different
from everyone else, that's all.
I'd advise you to
cut out the chatter...
Or else next time
I won't hit the wall.
[Black Star]
Hey, sorry I'm late.
[Stein]
Another fight?
Yeah. It's cool.
Miss Marie was the supervisor.
[Stein]
And... how'd it go?
I am the biggest star
in this academy...
Obviously, I won.
Winner or loser,
you're still late for class.
You can enjoy yourself
out here in the hallway.
[Black Star]
Dammit.
[Black Star thinks]
I have to get stronger.
What's been getting
into Black Star lately...?
He's fighting so much.
Yeah I know ten fights and
ten victories without
using his weapon.
Something's up.
[Stein] Like I told
you all last week,
we're going to be starting
a new lesson today,
so I hope you're ready.
As you know,
the Kishin's madness has
woken the witch Arachne...
And with her revival,
the organization Arachnophobia
is once again active.
So now it's time to
learn about Duel Arts.
It's simpler if I don't
explain it in words.
This lesson you'll learn
by doing, not listening.
Some of you are slower
than others, so we'll see.
He was looking at
us when he said that!
You aren't even really
embarrassed, are you?
All right, if I call your name,
please step to the
front of the classroom...
First up we have
Ox and Harvar...
Get down here.
Our newly recovered
student... Maka...
Sweet!
...with Soul, of course.
Lastly...
Black Star... get back in here.
In or out?
Make up your
mind already, woudja?
Uh... why are you all sweaty?
I'm concerned you may
destroy the classroom if you
use your weapon for this.
So you're on your own.
Up until this point,
your training
in resonating souls
has been exclusively with
your respective partners.
But the fact of the
matter is, you're still kids.
A single soul resonance likely
won't be enough against the
type of enemy we're facing now.
So, what I'm going to
teach you today is how to
work together to
resonate souls as a team.
All five of us are supposed
to match wavelengths?
I realize this is
a new concept for you...
...but give it a try anyway.
Come after me
with all you've got.
Already...? Just like that?
Bring it on...
I'll dissect you all.
Creepy!
Hell yeah!!
[Rachel]
Where's breakfast, Mommy?
I'm hungry!
Yes, I know you are dear...
It'll be ready soon.
There's plenty left
over for seconds.
It looks so yummy!
I guess it was my
imagination after all.
This is the best
Mother can do?
What a pathetically
boring and tasteless meal.
There's a spider...!
How did that filthy
thing get in here...?
Go on, get out now.
Arachne... It didn't take
her very long to notice.
Rachel what...?
Mommy...!
I'm going outside to play.
Hold it, Rachel!
Where are you going?
A good friend of mine
is waiting for me...
Let go.
Wait... who are you...?
You're not Rachel.
[Medusa switches to her
voice] What a bad mother,
treating your own daughter
like she's a stranger.
She's such a
good little girl, too...
...and so easily controlled.
No...!
Don't forget to lock
the doors and windows.
If they're open, snakes
and spiders will get in.
We don't want that.
Bye-bye, Mommy.
[Rachel's mother]
Rachel!
I have no idea how
this is done... Do you?
No clue...
But Stein's not messing
around this time...
We're just gonna have
to figure something out.
Let's go.
I still don't see how we're
supposed to match wavelengths
with these guys, but okay.
Die, you mad scientist wacko!
Four-eyed freak!
Anybody else want
in on the fun...?
Don't over think it.
It won't do you any good.
I can barely think at all with
this many people watching us.
Damn you--
All right... My turn!
Royal Thunder!
[Ox]
Huh?
Do you have
a death wish... huh?!
Hey man it's your own fault.
You're the one who jumped
in front of my attack.
Move it!
Maka...
You damn idiot!
My bad! Sorry, Black Star.
Royal Thunder!
[Ox]
Huh?
[laughing in classroom]
How pathetic.
That was even worse
than I'd expected.
I'm done with this.
[Black Star]
Professor,
I'm gonna beat the
crap out of Ox now.
Will you act
as fight supervisor?
[Stein] Save your
fighting for after class.
[Ox]
Whatever you say, Professor.
But Black Star and I are gonna
have to settle this eventually.
[Stein]
Why do I bother?
Do you think you stand
a chance against the
Royal Thunder Commander?
[Black Star]
Shut up!
That makes eleven straight
victories for Black Star.
But is it really a
victory if your
opponent was that pathetic?
[yelling in the classroom]
[Stein] I ask them
to work together
and they beat each
other up instead...
So much for that.
Even if we had all
the time in the world,
it still may not be enough...
They don't seem to get it.
[Naigus] What do
you think Lord Death's
reason is for keeping the
Book of Eibon in the vault?
[Sid] If he wanted us to know,
he would've told us...
Let it go.
This is Lord Death's
personal collection...
There's some pretty
frightening stuff down here.
Now, there's no
need to be shy...
Go ahead and drink it up.
A glass of fresh blood
should do the trick.
[Mosquito]
Thank you...
It's an honor, Lady Arachne.
[Giriko] Of course,
it might be poisoned.
I'm joking...
We can't kill you quite yet.
Unfortunately, we have to
keep you around if we want
to get the Book of Eibon back.
Forgive me, my lady.
The plans for the Magic Tool
were lost because of
my incompetence...
You can make it up to
me by doing better
next time, Mosquito...
Anyway, at least one good
thing came of your failure.
We were able to
test Mifune's abilities.
Yes... and I believe we'll
be able to put his
power to good use.
Is that your big plan...?
What good are you if
that's the only thing
you can come up with?
[Mosquito] I suggest you
watch your tone with me.
Got it, chainsaw boy?
My chains are getting dull.
Maybe I should sharpen
them on your body, old man.
Just try it!
I'll drain every drop of blood
from your body until you're
an empty sack of skin.
Police Stinger!
Yeah, fly away little bug.
That's all you can do...?
I hate to break it to you,
but you're past your prime.
Then maybe you'd like
to take a look at my form
from eight hundred years ago.
This is my Three-Piece
Police Stinger!
There's nothing better
than reclaiming
lost youth, is there...?
Shall I snap a picture for you?
Whatdya say?
Of course, it'll be an
awkward portrait with you
cut up into little bits and all.
You young punk!
Old fool!
[fighting sounds]
[Eruka]
Lady Arachne!
Yes, what is it now?
[Eruka] There's a guest
waiting to see you.
[Arachne]
A guest...? Who is it?
[Eruka] Forgive me,
Lady Arachne...
...but she keeps insisting
that she's your little sister.
I see... Very well...
Show her in.
[Arachne chuckles]
[Arachne]
My, my. Look at you.
What an adorable body you
found this time, Medusa.
[Medusa]
How sweet that you still
remember me after
eight hundred long years.
[Arachne]
How could I forget you...?
I always make sure
to keep you in my sights,
no matter how
many centuries pass.
[Medusa] It seems you're still
as good a spy as ever Arachne.
[Arachne] You haven't
changed a bit, either...
Still barging in here
without warning,
not showing an ounce of fear.
You'll never learn, will you...?
Not even in that dreadful
new form you have.
Oh, but you can get away
with a lot in this body.
I find your determination
truly inspiring.
You were badly hurt
during that fight
at the academy...
Your soul was torn into pieces,
but here you stand,
alive and well.
I knew there was one thing
I had to avoid at any cost.
At no point could I allow
Stein and Death Scythe
to swallow my soul.
When I took that final blow...
I split my soul into pieces...
...entered a snake...
...and repaired myself,
so that I could
return once more.
[Arachne] That was
a dangerous move,
even for a powerful
witch like yourself...
You survived out of sheer luck.
[Medusa]
You're probably right...
The revival of the Kishin Asura
caused the release of
strong madness wavelengths...
My magic was able
to feed off of their power.
It's likely I wouldn't
survive that again.
[Arachne] So what brings
you here, Medusa?
I fought the Grim Reaper
eight hundred years ago until,
at the very end of the battle...
...someone betrayed me.
You think you can just drop
in here and leave again
without paying a price?
It's silly to cling to
the past like that...
The two of us should be friends.
We're a pair of newly
revived sisters, after all.
[Medusa laughs]
How thoughtful!
A surprise party to welcome
me back to the world?
But it's so sudden,
and I'm afraid
I'm no good at parties.
I'll see you again soon, though,
dear sister of mine.
She always was
an obnoxious girl.
[Eruka] I'll see
her out, my lady.
Are you sure... about her?
I'll let her play her
games for awhile.
In the end she'll be caught
in my web like everybody else.
[Eruka]
You can't just show up
here like that whenever
you want to, Medusa...!
If you're not careful,
you're going to
get me discovered!
You'll continue surveillance
as instructed.
Is that understood... Eruka?
[Eruka]
Yes ma'am.
I thought after this
she'd finally let me go!
[Medusa] Freedom
always comes at a price.
[Eruka]
So... uh...
...what're you going to do now?
I'm borrowing this.
I have to retrieve something
precious that I left behind.
In Death City.
♪ closing song ♪
Maka here.
Next week Kid and the
others get in big trouble.
Medusa here.
As you can see,
due to popular demand,
I've returned!
[Maka] I like studying.
[Medusa] I like experiments.
[Maka]
I do the Maka Chop.
[Medusa] I lie and
hurt people a lot.
[Maka]
It may be hard to believe,
but next week you'll see
we have something in common.
[Medusa] Hmm,
how should we put this?
[Both] Neither of us is
in the next episode!
[Medusa] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Red Hot Runaway Express!
o~A Magic Tool Left
Behind by the Grand Wizard?o~
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!