[Maka] A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[ominous slow breeze]
R-Run away!
The black dragon!
The black dragon is here!
♪ opening song ♪
[Patty]
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
♪ gently down the stream. ♪
[Kid] Come on.
Can't you row any faster?
Will you explain to me
what we're doing in a
rowboat in the first place?!
Why not a motor boat
or a nice, big cruise ship.
You know--
something with an engine maybe?!
[Kid]
Quit complaining.
Anyway... We've almost
reached our destination now.
That's where we're going?
[Patty] ♪ Row your boat
gently down the stream... ♪
[Liz] That's a nice-enough
looking village, I guess...
Seems pretty peaceful.
I'm not so sure about that.
Why...? The place
looks okay to me.
[Kid]
Look over there.
What the heck happened?
[Kid]
A few days ago,
the people who lived here
were swallowed up by something.
[Liz]
Along with their homes...
Please don't tell me
we're here to find out
what was responsible.
Let's go...
We need to gather information.
Can you tell me
what happened here?
[Man A]
It was the mist.
[Kid]
Mist?
What do you mean?
What kind of mist?
[Man A]
No... No...!
[Kid]
Calm down... Don't worry...
You're all right now.
We're here to help you.
We've come from the DWMA to
put a stop to whatever did this.
[Man A]
The academy?
[Kid]
Yes.
So please tell me in as
much detail as you can
what happened here.
Black... Black Dragon...
The black dragon came...
The black dragon came
and ate our village!
[Man A screams]
[Kid]
The black dragon...
Interesting.
[Maka] The Soul-eating
Black Dragon...
Scaredy-cat Liz and
Her Merry Friends?
[Patty]
Elephant... chimpanzee...
...dog... cat!
[Liz]
Very good...
...but aren't you a little
old for picture books?
Coo-coo-coo.
Lemme guess...
a pigeon?
Oink! Oink!
Yeah, and that was a pig.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Come on, Kid...
Tell me we're done with
this musty old place.
It's suffocating in here.
[Kid]
Don't be such a slacker...
Preliminary research
is necessary.
Which is what I would tell
you if I didn't
hate this place too.
I think I've got
enough basic information.
Let's go.
We need to get started.
Good... So then what's
our next destination?
Ooh-eee!
[Patty] ♪ Row, row,
row your boat
gently down the
stream, etc... ♪
[Kid] You can row harder
than that, can't you?
Why are we back
in this stupid rowboat?
Whatever we're going to do,
it'd better be real
important, or else...!
[Kid]
Of course it is...
Would I make you work
this hard for nothing?
Well knowing you... yes...
So... what is this black
dragon thing we're after?
[Kid] This part of the Baltic
Sea is a key maritime area.
There has been a lot of
boat traffic out here...
Sailors have been crossing
these waters since
the Vikings first set sail.
Kay... but what
does that have to
do with some scary
black dragon?
Not every boat
makes it to shore.
So, in an area where there
are many ships crossing...
That means there are also
a number of ships sinking.
Kid, I don't think I like
where this is heading...
[Kid] Just because a ship sinks
doesn't mean it'll stay sunk.
[Liz]
What is this?
[Patty]
A cloud!
[Kid]
It's mist.
[Liz] What kind of mist?
[Kid] We're getting close.
Stay sharp.
[Liz]
What?!
[Kid] I sense the presence of
countless numbers of
souls in this area.
[Liz]
So what does that mean?
[Liz cries out in panic]
[Kid] It means that's
the black dragon.
[Liz]
What is that thing?!
See that writing?
[Patty]
Ni... duh... hogg?
[Kid] Nidhogg is the name
of a black dragon that
appears in Norse Mythology.
According to the legend,
it's also the name of a
ghost ship that
haunts these waters...
Many people have believed
the legend to be true.
And now I can
see why they would.
Right...!
Ladies, let's go...
we're heading up there!
No, no way, not a chance.
It's a ghost ship...!
Which means there're
gonna be ghosts on it!
[Patty]
Row!
Wait Patty...!
Patty! Patty! Patty! Patty!
[Kid] You idiot...I told you
to wait, didn't I?
[Patty giggles]
Whoopsie... sorry!
If you want to do
damage to the other ship,
you have to ram
them in the middle!
[Patty]
Uh-oh.
You're mad cause she
didn't hit the middle?!
Now, do it again!
Oh-kay!
Huh?!
[Patty]
Row!
[Kid]
Okay... let's board.
[Liz] You guys
are absolutely crazy.
Worse than crazy,
you're insane crazy jerks.
Insane, crazy jerks
with a death wish.
Oh no-oo...! I was so busy
focusing on their insanity
that I came on board.
I'm gonna die!
[Liz cries]
[Kid]
From what I'm sensing,
the souls are inside
the ship somewhere...
In we go.
Yay!
[Liz]
I've got a better idea:
how 'bout we don't?
There are ghosts hanging
around in there, remember...?
What if they eat us...?
Hey, guys, are
you listening to me...?
You guys!
[Kid]
Let's go, Liz.
[Captain laughs evilly]
A fresh batch of souls have
come to me all on their own!
[Kid]
They're just ahead.
[Liz shivers and panics]
[door creak]
[Kid]
All these human souls...
Whatever someone
has planned, it isn't good.
Can we take all these
souls cause they
don't belong to anyone?
Idiot...! Do you want
to become a Kishin...?
As a protector of souls,
I can't allow this.
I have to safeguard them.
What do
we have here...?
You're a grim reaper?
Liz... Patty!
Yeah, okay.
Okay!
Nid... hogg!
[Liz screams]
Liz wait!
[Patty giggles]
She fell...! She fell!
She's your sister!
How can you be
laughing like that?!
[Captain laughs]
This ship is my body,
and my body is this ship.
All I have to do
is digest the little lady.
[Kid]
Are you an evil spirit...?
What are you planning
to do with all these
human souls you've gathered?
[Captain] The meddlesome Lord
Death is making things more
difficult for me
than ever before...
That's why I'm going to present
these souls to the Kishin...
I'll certainly be
rewarded for that.
[Kid]
Kishin?
You mean the sword Ragnarok?
[Captain laughs]
That rookie doesn't have
anything to do with this...
No, no, I'm talking about
the Kishin who's
right next to you.
That's who I gathered
these souls for.
What's that...?
What do you mean next to us?
[Captain laughs]
It's nothing a child
like you would understand.
This ship and I have
things to do, people to see...
We're going places together,
me and this ship...
Somewhere at sea, far away...
people are waiting to
hear the song of the Kishin.
Most people are alike...
They all crave power
in one form or another...
but for some...
no amount of earthly power
will ever be
enough to satisfy...
They always hunger for more.
It's humans like these
who are seeking the Kishin...
and these souls
that you see here
are my own offering to it...
They're not for you, boy!
Hey, Kid...
I'm gonna transform now.
No.
I can't.
I can't I can't
I can't I can't.
I can't do this!
[Liz]
Patty...! Kid...!
Where are you...?
I hope the ghosts
haven't eaten you!
Kid won't be able to
use Patty without me.
It would be asymmetrical.
He'd get a nosebleed
and pass out.
There's no way they'll
be able to fight whatever's
on this creepy ship...
I have to get back
to them quickly.
Okay... I'm not the
least bit frightened!
No way is this ghost
ship scary to me!
I'm one of the Thompson sisters,
the legendary devils of
Brooklyn nobody wants to
run into in a dark alley...!
Nothing frightens me...!
Nothing!
[Liz panics]
What am I doing on this ship?
How did this happen to me?!
Just our luck that we went
and mugged a grim reaper...
Life isn't fair!
Where am I going?
Is this even the right way?
[Girl]
Yes it is... This way.
[Liz]
(oh) Hey, thanks.
That's very nice of you.
Who said that?!
I'm just hearing
things, that's all.
[Girl]
You're doing well...
Just keep coming
straight this way.
I won't look. I won't look.
If I don't look, she'll go away.
No one's there. No one's there.
No one's there.
Oh please, let no one be there!
I won't look.
[Girl] Come on...
just a little further this way.
I'm the spirit of a girl
who was eaten by this ship...
Don't worry,
I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm not dumb.
I know how ghosts work.
You were eaten, and now you're
angry and restless
and you want revenge.
So you're gonna eat me!
I don't have any
reason to eat you...
I only want to help you...
If you'll just follow me,
I can take you back
to your friends, okay?
I can see through you!
You're lying!
You want gobble up my hot body!
No, I'm not going to eat you...
You just have to trust me.
I might have big boobs,
but I'm all skin and bones!
Just trust me.
I'd be stringy and tough
and not tasty at all, I promise.
Just trust me.
[Liz cries out]
Okay, that's enough...
Quit your childish blathering
and follow me right now...!
Or I'll spank you to death!
Yes ma'am...
I'll follow you anywhere.
I'm glad we got
that straightened out...
Now get moving.
[Girl]
For crying out loud,
I don't see what you have
to be so upset about anyway!
I didn't even get to live
long enough to have
a hot body like you.
Oh yeah...
I'm sorry I rubbed
it in, really.
Patty... your big sis
ain't doin' so well.
Running away won't do any good.
[Kid thinks] I partnered with
these two specifically so
something like
this wouldn't happen.
I need symmetry...!
Maybe I should have
listened to my father!
He tried to pick out
a good weapon for me...
But I refused to listen to him.
Stubborn!
All I cared about...
All I wanted...
Was symmetry...!
Two symmetrical weapons!
Was that so much to ask for?!
And now all my efforts...
Have been completely...
and utterly... wasted!
Damn it!
Where did Liz go?
Hey... This way...
Come this way... La...dy.
--This way, Lady....
--Quit screaming, you big baby!
--Come this way...
--I'm too young to die!
--Follow the arrows.
--Please don't make
me come with you!
[Captain] What's
the matter, boy...?
Shouldn't a grim reaper
have more power than this?
You haven't seen
what I can do yet!
Then why not
show me something...?
Are you frightened,
reaper boy...?
I worship the Kishin,
your sworn enemy.
And I steal the souls
of innocent people.
This is the perfect chance
to pass judgment on
what you call evil.
[Kid]
I do not deny evil,
nor do I believe that any
human is completely
free of malice.
Everything must be in balance.
As long as evil and good
maintain an equilibrium
in this world,
there is no problem...
Perfect balance is
the key to everything.
Who cares about the
ideals of some stupid kid?
Don't think for one second
that all humans feel
the same way you do!
I don't care if
they do or not...!
I'm going to keep fighting
until this world is
the way it should be...
Until the world is balanced.
Really...? Even if that
means taking away freedom?
[Kid]
You disgust me!
I am a grim reaper...
I refuse to grant anyone
the freedom to kill.
[Ghosts]
Come this way...
come this way...
This is the way.
Here we are.
Thanks a lot for all your help.
[Liz] We're up
on deck, all right...
...but I don't see anybody else.
I knew it!
I was right all along!
You are going to eat me.
You're going to simmer me
in a pot with onions and garlic
and have me for dinner!
They're coming right now.
Stop crying or
I will smack you!
[Patty]
Oh, hi Sis!
[Kid]
Hey there Liz...
Nice of you to show up...!
You idiot! Because of you,
I couldn't use Patty,
you know that!
It's not my fault
that you're crazy.
You're... back...!!
Patty!
I missed you so much!
[Captain laughs]
You aren't goin' to get away.
Finally.
Now that we're all
back together,
we can take care of business.
Liz... Patty...
Time to transform...Let's go.
O'Kay!
Yeah. Okay.
Time to die.
What was that?
The sword.
Ragnarok.
Scream Resonance.
[Ragnarok lets out
a deafening scream]
[Crona cries out]
What the--
The souls are coming out now.
[Crona bellows]
I have to go...
Goodbye dumb scardey-cat lady.
[Kid]
This can't be possible!
He devoured all
of the human souls.
He musta been real hungry, huh?
Bastard.
[Crona cries out during
transformation]
I think we're looking at
the Demon Sword's true form.
Hey, you're icky and gross!!
What is he...?
There's nothing human
about that thing up there.
[Kid] In this region
of the Baltic Sea,
there was once a legend
believed by many about a
ghost ship called
the black dragon.
However...
This thing in front of us...
This Demon Sword...
Is a true black dragon.
[Crona]
Hey...
My blood is black you know.
I judge you.
Reaper Combat Art:...
"Mortal Sin" Stance.
[Ragnarok screams out]
It's time to die.
♪ closing song ♪
[Captain] Nidhogg,
let's take care of these
guys and get back
down under the sea.
[Kid] Before you go,
Flying Dutchman,
I have a question for you...
Tell me... can you really fly?
[Captain]
Why do you ask that?
[Kid]
What else would I ask...?
Come on, tell me.
Are you able to fly or not?
[Captain] Well, if you must
know, it's more like floating.
[Kid] I knew it...!
You're a phony...!
You can't really fly.
All you can do is float!
[Captain] What should
I do about it?
[Kid]
Change your name!
[Kid] On the next episode
of Soul Eater
Fierce Battle Aboard
the Ghost Ship...
The Hell Inside My Head?