[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[winding and clicking]
[Death] He was unquestionably
the greatest meister to ever
graduate from the academy...
Dr. Franken Stein...
He's a tough one.
[Kid]
So this meister was
your weapon Death
Scythe's first partner...
[Liz] And wait-- you sent
a group of students
to go collect his soul?
He should send you,
big sis-- you could do it!
Only if I really
felt like dying...
You're overestimating
me a little bit, Patty...
I wouldn't last two seconds...
These are remedial
lessons, right?
Aren't you asking
a bit too much?
[Death groans]
You know what's
going to happen...
They'll die.
♪ opening song ♪
[Soul] So this is
where we find Stein.
Let's hurry and
finish this guy off...
I'm ready for these
lessons to be over.
[winding and clicking]
He even put zigzag
stitches on his laboratory.
[beeps and clicking]
Interesting architecture.
I wonder what kind
of guy this Stein is.
Something's coming
out of there.
[Stein yelps as he falls]
[Stein]
Damn it...
Still doesn't feel quite right.
[Stein]
Hmm...
Maybe that'll take care of it.
Okay...
I'm gonna try that again.
Um...
Shouldn't someone stop him?
But we just met him.
Isn't that rude?
I'd like to see what
happens next.
Yeah, so would I.
[Stein yelps as he falls]
[All think]
Is this guy for real?
[Maka] Shape of the Soul--
Enter the Ultimate
Meister, Stein?
[Stein] Was there something
you kids needed me for?
Yeah if you're really Dr. Stein.
You did this...
You're the one who
turned Sid into a zombie.
[Stein]
Oh... so that's it...
I'm guessing you guys are
all students from
the academy then?
[Maka]
Why did you do this?
Revenge? A grudge?
No, nothing like that...
I have a simpler motive:
experimentation and observation.
That's all a true
scientist cares about.
And, I am a scientist.
Everything in the world is
an experimental test subject...
Of course that includes
myself as well.
Hey, do you feel that, Soul...?
I think something
strange is happening.
[Soul]
Huh...? Like what?
[Stein] Your souls' wavelengths
aren't very stable...
What's more, they're quite
different from one another...
I see one soul that is
careless and arrogant
and one that is earnest
and strong-willed.
They appear to be in
resonance, but they aren't.
What the hell...?
You mean you can see
the soul of someone
who's still alive...?
In that case,
you must be a meister.
He was able to read the
character of the souls, too...
Only the best
meisters can do that.
So what...
Maka you can see souls
clearly like that too... Right?
Oh... Well, of course I can!
Your soul seems confused
by that last statement...
How cute.
Shut up! Quit it!
Stop looking at
my soul, you creep!
[Black Star] Yeah, shut up,
little doctor man...
No one wants to hear
you talk anymore...
Hya-hoo...!
How about we change the
subject to a more
interesting
conversation topic...?
Like me, for example...
[Tsubaki]
When did he...
Who cares if you can see souls?
What does that matter, huh...?
Not like you're gonna
see anything interesting...
Far as I'm concerned,
the only soul worth
lookin' at is mine!
[Stein laughs]
Yours is an interesting one.
Your soul is extremely
self-centered
and more than a little bit wild.
It must be rather difficult
to find a partner with a
soul that's compatible
with your own, isn't it?
No more talking.
Black Star!
Hmm?
Ah, yes I see it now.
You must be the
wild one's partner.
You're always willing
to compromise,
and possess a
very accepting nature.
It makes sense that you're
the one who's able to cooperate
with his soul's wavelength.
Who do you think
you are old man?
[Stein] Now that I've collected
the necessary initial data
from all of you...
I think we're ready
to begin the experiment.
[Death Scythe sobs]
[Death Scythe] Looks
like we've run out of sake.
[Blair] You drink so fast
I can hardly keep up.
Hold on for just a sec...
Pum-Pum-pumpkin,
pumpkin, and up we go!
Blair, you're already
so good at this,
and it's only your third
day working here...
I would have guessed
you've been here forever.
Really? Aww, thank you!
[Blair] You went to the
school today didn't you...?
How'd it go...?
How were things with Maka?
She ignored me!
Oh you poor thing.
It doesn't matter what I do...
She just gets angry.
Maka is such a darling girl...
Anyway, your divorce from her
mother was finalized
last month, wasn't it?
It's time to move on.
Let's see if we can
cheer you up... Kay?
What do I have to
be cheerful about...?
Custody goes to the mother...
My wife... no, no...
My ex wife won't let me
contribute anything.
No alimony or
medical expenses...
What could I ever
be to Maka now?
I'm a father without
any fatherly duties.
Doesn't mean
you're not her dad...
being a parent is about more
than just money, isn't it?
You should fight for her.
But spending money is a way
of expressing
love too, right...?
It's just so frustrating not
being able to do
anything for her.
Okay then, think
about it this way...
With all that extra money,
you'll be able to indulge
in your bad habits
more than usual.
Plus, maybe we can even
find you a new wife...!
Let's get going !
I can't do that...
I've never even
thought about remarrying.
This is the worst day
I've had since I was
assigned Stein as a partner.
This is not good,
Blair, really...!
You're depressing the customer.
Meow!
[Stein] You must be
Scythe Meister Maka.
[Black Star]
Ow. My face!
Hmm... Let's see,
Scythe Meister Maka...
something's familiar
about that name.
If I could just
put my finger on it...
Ah...! Your mother
was a meister,
and you're Spirit's
little daughter, aren't you?
It was an absolute hell...
The time I spent as his partner.
[Soul]
Who's Spirit?
That's what my father
was called before he
became a death scythe...
But I wanna know how
you knew about that.
I can still remember,
even now...
He looked so
peaceful in his sleep.
That guy... he did...
experiments on my body!
He used me as a lab rat
while I was sleeping.
And this went
on for five years!
Wow... for five years?
I can't believe you
didn't notice anything.
Oh, wow...!
You must've been
really stupid back then.
The only strange thing
I noticed was that new scars
would appear on
my body every day.
If my ex wife hadn't
figured out what was going on,
he might still be
doing things to me...!
I can't stand to think
about it even now!
Ah... so...
You are indeed Spirit's
darling little daughter.
And the daughter of the
woman who ended
my greatest experiment.
I wonder what kind
of subject you'd make.
But you were
Stein's weapon partner
for five whole years,
weren't you...?
Doesn't that mean your
soul must have been
compatible with his?
You don't understand...
It doesn't matter...
If he has any
interest in a weapon,
he can easily master it.
He's much stronger and
smarter than my wife,
sorry, ex wife...
The one who made
me into a Death Scythe.
Stein's mad, but he's a genius.
[Soul] It's just a tap...
we can block it.
Okay.
What... what did he--
[Soul] What the hell
did he do to me?
[Kid]
I don't believe this...
Sure, magic weapons have
valuable physical attack
properties, but primarily,
a meister needs a weapon
to channel his soul
wavelength...
But that man...
he can attack with
his soul directly...
He doesn't need a weapon
to access his power...
[Death] Yup. The relationship
between meister and weapon
is a lot like the
relationship between
a guitar and an amplifier.
[Death] On its own...
an electric guitar is only
capable of emitting
a small noise.
But when you connect the
guitar to an amplifier,
you enhance the sound waves...
and the result is much
more powerful than before.
[Death]
Witch Hunter.
The technique that Maka
used in the battle against
Sid is a perfect
example of this.
Even if she did fail
with it in the end.
But in Stein's case...
he can use the guitar to
make a huge noise
without an amplifier.
That's incredible.
[Kid] I can only
imagine how
strong he must be when
he does use a weapon.
Let's see here...
How should I begin
my experiment?
[Soul]
What's wrong, Maka...?
Chill out.
Your soul waves
are completely chaotic!
[Maka bellows]
[Soul]
Wait, Maka.
That was a dumb move.
Maka.
Ahh... You have lovely skin.
Simply lovely...
Where do you think I
should insert the knife first?
Let's see if I can turn your
smooth skin into sandpaper.
[Black Star]
You're about to need a
new pair of glasses, bastard!
How could you've already
forgotten that I'm here?
[Stein]
Easily.
[Black Star] You're not the only
one who can use soul waves
to attack without a weapon!
[Stein]
What?
[Black Star]
Black Star Big Wave!!
Amazing!
He can do that?
[Death] He may
appear to be a child,
but Black Star's soul wavelength
is incredibly large...
And for his age,
he's a genius at using the
direct soul attack
against an opponent.
Still... It won't do him
much good in this fight.
A surprise from
the wild boy.
What the hell is going on?
[Soul] This is useless.
You deflected my soul attack.
[Stein]
Don't you remember how
I checked your soul data
when you first arrived here...?
When I did that,
I familiarized myself
with your soul's wavelength,
so now I can adjust
mine so that they match...
When the wavelengths
are the same,
they cancel each other out
so your attack is powerless.
You see in the exact
moment you attacked...
We temporarily bonded...
It's like the connection between
a meister and his weapon.
A human can actually
accomplish that?
[Death]
It's only possible if the
human has a soul that is
incredibly flexible...
Stein does... That's one of the
reasons that he is so
difficult to defeat in a fight.
That was a fun experiment,
but now it's my turn.
[Black Star screams]
Black Star!
Leave him alone!
[Soul, Maka and Tsubaki]
Black Star!
This is too much...
They need help. Let's go.
Okay, sure.
Leeeet's go!
[Death] Kid, you
can't get involved.
This is a test for them
to complete on their own...
Besides, you're a Grim Reaper...
You're not a student here.
[Kid] Alright...
Then in that case,
as of this moment,
consider me enrolled.
Dad, I would appreciate it
if you would register
me for classes...
Liz, Patty.
Yes, Kid.
Yes. Kid.
[Death]
Hey, all of you!
Come back here!
Oh my, my...
[Soul]
What did he do?
Tsubaki... You know that I was
never a man to run away...
...but you shouldn't fight
a battle that cannot be won.
You should go.
Damn you, Stein.
You won't get away with this.
I'll kill you!
Right...
Let's go and get him, Maka.
No way.
Huh...? What's wrong?
This is impossible.
The little girl can
see my soul, huh?
[Maka]
We can't...
...the difference between
us is too great.
Hey, come on...!
What's wrong with you, Maka?
[Maka] I can't...
He'll defeat me.
No, I can't go on like this...
I should die.
We get to do this some more?
[Kid]
How could this happen...?!
Did I really forget to fold
the tip of the toilet paper
into a triangle?!
You don't know if you forgot...?
You always do, so why
would you forget this time?
You really are a
prissy little girl sometimes...
Seriously Kid!
[Patty]
Here we go again!
If you don't hurry
and snap out of it,
those kids are gonna die...
Who cares about what
happened with the toilet paper?
[Kid] How could
you not care...?
I'm a failure!
A complete failure...!
What kind of Grim Reaper
am I if I can't even
remember to fold
the toilet paper?
I can't take over
my father's position...
What kind of son am I...?
He'll probably disown me.
That's not true, Kid.
You'll take over,
and you'll probably be
the best Grim Reaper ever...
You know what we should do?
Run right over there to
that creepy laboratory
and save those kids.
Come on! Let's go!
[Kid]
No.
What?! Why?!
What if I didn't fold
the toilet paper?
Something like that could
ruin my life forever.
I can't be defeated
by toilet paper!
If I turn my back on this
I shouldn't be allowed
to live anymore.
Then die already!
[Soul] What's the matter
with you, Maka?!
Why are you just
sitting there? Get up!
[Maka] Shut up!
You wouldn't be acting so
tough if you could see the
shape of his soul like I can!
You're wrong!
I wouldn't care, Maka...
All you saw was
a single soul, right?
You didn't see your future.
You can't give up
before you even fight...
You're supposed to turn me
into the strongest
Death Scythe ever...
You don't want that
worthless father of yours
to outshine us, do you?
Look up and listen to me...!
Do you hear me, Maka?
I'm talking to you!
Good. Now look over there
and tell me what you see.
He's been waiting patiently for
you to finish
this temper tantrum.
Isn't that so polite
of the good Doctor Stein?
Come on...
If we die, we die cool.
Sorry about that...
I'm better now.
No problem.
Let's go! Soul Resonance!
[Stein thinks] The
resonance of the souls.
Meister and weapon harmonize...
The meister passes
soul waves to the weapon...
The weapon then magnifies
the waves and passes them back.
They repeat this process
until they create a soul wave
more powerful than
either is alone.
[Soul] Let's keep this up
until we reach our limit.
Yeah, okay.
[Stein thinks]
I'm impressed...
She can use the Witch Hunter
when she's still so young.
[Stein] You're putting
everything into one hit?
Come on...!
Let's see exactly how much
your souls can handle.
The legendary super skill
of the scythe meister!
Witch Hunter!
[Stein] You can control the
Witch Hunter, too...
But I'm afraid your
skills are too rough.
[Maka]
Soul.
[Stein] You managed
to remain conscious.
Back away...
I won't let you
touch my meister.
In that case,
I'll start with you.
You earned a passing grade.
Good job.
Huh?
[Stein] Your extra lessons
have been completed.
You gave up your own
body to protect your meister...
That's all you need to
earn a pass from me.
Sorry, maybe I wasn't
clear the first time.
I'll say it again... Huh?
This was all planned
out by Lord Death...
He asked me to do him a favor...
He wanted me to help you
with these extra lessons.
But if you were in on it,
why did you kill Black Star?
I bet you think
you're a funny guy, huh?
He's still alive...
But what about Sid the zombie?
Ah, yeah,
sorry about all this...
...back when I was alive
I was definitely a man who
would never tell a lie.
But a lot of things
have changed since then.
Ah, you don't say...!
Then what the hell
was the point of all this?!
To see if you could
scare us to death?!
Seriously?
[Death] But you're better now
than before, aren't you?
It was just a test...
But I confess it was fun
scaring you kids like that.
You should've seen your faces!
That man is seriously sadistic.
Hey everyone,
I'm sure you're all tired.
Why don't you spend
the night in my laboratory.
That's a big fat "no"!
I'm still worn out
from last night.
[Maka] I dreamt Stein was using
me in his experiments.
Tsubaki...!
Was Stein a bigger star
than me yesterday?!
[Tsubaki]
Seriously?
I wonder if they've
hired a new teacher
to replace Sid yet...
Hey, maybe your dad
will be our teacher again.
No! Anyone but him.
[Stein bellows out]
[Stein]
All right class...
Are we ready to get started?
This isn't funny.
This might be the first time...
I've actually wanted
to see my father.
Damn, that guy sure
knows how to get attention.
We're gonna start by
dissecting some frogs.
Should be pretty exciting.
♪ ending song ♪
[Maka] Ah! I thought
I was gonna die.
[Kid] The best lessons are the
ones you think are real.
[Maka] Humph. Maybe you
should try it, then.
[Kid] In the
next episode, I will.
Running late on the first day
of school and then
plunged into a fight.
At that point it's
all about symmetry.
[Maka] That doesn't seem
to make any sense.
[Kid] Symmetry...
it's the beauty of symmetry.
[Maka] Nope, I still have no
idea what you're saying.
[Kid] On the next episode
of Soul Eater:
The New Student:
Kid's First Day at the Academy.
Will it be an
entrance to remember?
Symmetry is the
truest form of beauty.
[Maka] Hey,
that's where my line goes!