[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Maka] Tsubaki and Black Star
have been sent to the
village of Shin to hunt
the Enchanted Sword,
a weapon who teeters on
the brink of becoming a Kishin.
The Enchanted Sword
possesses whoever wields it...
taking over their body,
controlling their shadow...
...and eventually
devouring their soul.
There is a reason
why this pair...
...who have yet to collect
a single Kishin soul...
...were sent to complete such
a dangerous and deadly mission.
Tsubaki.
Hi brother.
[Maka]
Tsubaki is the only one
who can defeat the
Enchanted Sword.
♪ opening song ♪
[Black Star]
You've gone inside the
Enchanted Sword, huh, Tsubaki?
Ryoku.
What happened? Is he okay?
[Old Man] This is
the Star clan's fault...
Look what they've
done to Ryoku!
[Villager A]
It's terrible!
[Brat] Get out of our
village, murderer!
Tsubaki.
[Brat]
Did you hear me...?
I said, get out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Okay, just make
sure you come back.
[Maka] Tsubaki,
the Camellia Blossom
~What Lies Beyond the Grief?
[Tsubaki cries out
as she attacks]
[Masamune]
You're powerless...
What's the matter, Tsubaki?
I know you didn't
come just to visit,
so why aren't you attacking?
You are just like
your namesake,
the camellia blossom.
[Tsubaki cries out]
A flower without fragrance...
It proclaims nothing,
but blooms in pathetic silence.
When your petals scatter,
it is quietly tragic.
[Masamune]
Such a boring flower.
Do you know what I think?
I think if this was
the outside world,
you'd be dead by now.
What's the matter...?
Your soul's trembling...
What do you fear?
Is it death?
[Tsubaki] I may die today...
But I will stop you.
Don't look at me.
Stop it...! Those eyes...!
It was you...
You're the one
who led me here.
You brought me to the
path of the Enchanted Sword.
Get out! Get out! Get out!
[Old Man]
Bloodthirsty monster!
[Death] Black Star's showing
more restraint with those two
than I thought was
possible for him.
I can't believe Tsubaki
and the sword are
brother and sister.
But Black Star
still has no idea
about that, does he?
[Death]
(mm-mm)...
He trusts her...
...and for now that's
all he needs to know.
Tsubaki isn't moving...
Are you sure she's all right...?
What's she doing
in there, anyway?
[Death]
Hmm...
Well you see,
it's like this...
We brought snacks, everybody!
--Snacks at a time like this?!
--Gimme gimme gimme gimme!
What are you
two ditzes thinking?
[Stein] Let's see.
How should I put this...
To describe it simply...
Tsubaki is engaged in a
sort of soul tug-of-war with
the Enchanted Sword Masamune.
[Stein] As her brother makes
his move to possess her soul,
Tsubaki is countering by
trying to absorb his...
The struggle will continue
until one soul defeats
the other and wins.
Tsubaki's using his own
technique against him...
Nice... but do you think she
has any chance of winning?
[Stein] It will
be difficult for her.
It's the sword's soul,
so he's got home
court advantage...
and Soul Possession is one
of his trademark techniques...
Yeah... Altogether, the chance
that Tsubaki will win is low.
Brother and sister locked
in a fight to the death!
I can't even imagine it!
I couldn't go on living
without you, Patty!
There, there.
[Stein] A person who chooses
the path of the Kishin
reveals his own weakness...
The original Kishin sought
power in order to
escape the fear of death.
Why has Tsubaki's brother
chosen this path to power...?
What does he seek to
gain by becoming a Kishin?
[Masamune] You have
so many other options.
You could use your smoke
bomb or shuriken modes.
But you stick with
your plain old kasarigama.
Why are you holding back?
Pity...? Do you pity me?
[Stein]
Tsubaki and Masamune both
come from the
Nakatsukasa family...
That clan possesses
special weapon
abilities that are handed
down through the generations.
The previous generation's
abilities should have been
passed down to Masamune,
as he was the eldest son...
But instead...
You inherited everything
that should have gone
to me by birth right...
I inherited only one thing...
This sword.
For some reason,
the power was given to Tsubaki.
[Masamune] As a child
I was treated more
delicately than other boys.
I was babied for so long...
I got whatever I asked for,
but I never realized it was
because I was inferior...
In the end,
the one who showed me
that sad truth... was you.
[Masamune]
The pity in your eyes.
That's how you looked
at me when we were children,
when you hid your own
emotions because you
thought you were the strong one.
I'll never forgive you for that.
[Masamune]
Tsubaki... dear sister...
I'm going to kill you.
I will become a Kishin...
[Masamune]
And then...
I will master this sword.
[Masamune]
Puppet Rain.
[Tsubaki in pain]
Black Star...
[Black Star]
Tsubaki.
[mob beating Black Star]
[Black Star] Remember
our entrance ceremony
at the academy...?
The incredible
performance I gave...?
I remember it perfectly.
Yahoo!
Fellow students...
remember this well!
I am Black Star,
the world's greatest
assassin...!
The big man...!
I will transcend death!
--Is that a jumper?
--Or an idiot?
[Black Star] I'll achieve
greatness beyond your
wildest dreams!
Try not to feel too bad
about living in my shadow...
It isn't your fault that
I'm the biggest star ever!
Sooner or later you
will all cower before me!
Let me hear you now...!
Scream the name of Black Star!
[Black Star]
(Hmph)...
It looks like this world might
not be ready for me yet.
Wow... That was amazing.
Yeah.
You're the first person
to appreciate my talent...
Good for you...
You'll go far...
Now, what's your name?
Oh!
Tsubaki... I'm a weapon.
I'm the world's greatest
assassin, Black Star.
I'm a meister.
[Black Star] That was
the first time we met...
You watched my performance
all the way through
to the end that day.
Now it's my turn to see
you all the way through.
[Brat]
Who's this woman?
She's been sitting
there for a long time.
You're with him aren't you...?
Well you can get
out of our village too!
[Black Star]
Listen, you little brat...
Don't even think
about interrupting Tsubaki
again or I'll kill you?
You got me?
Just sit there and
keep your mouth shut.
Oh yeah well
screw you Star clan!
[Masamune] Do you have any
last words before I kill you?
You truly are a pathetic little
camellia blossom, aren't you?
Nothing to say.
Hey Tsubaki, what do you
feel like playing today?
[Tsubaki]
Whatever you want to.
Come on, Tsubaki.
You always want
to play my game,
what do you want to play?
Okay... I want to play ball.
And now Tsubaki, your soul...
...belongs to me.
[stabbing sound]
[Maka] What's Tsubaki thinking,
taking him on all alone?
[Stein] Tsubaki is a powerful,
adaptable weapon...
She's very good
at what she does...
But this time,
her opponent is too strong.
I should've been the one
to face the Enchanted Sword.
But she's not really alone.
[Soul] Black Star's sitting
right next to her...
And he won't budge.
Tsubaki wouldn't be
able to fight if he wasn't
there with her, would she?
[Death]
Right.
What's important now
is what's in here...
We all know Tsubaki's an
incredibly versatile weapon...
She has many modes of attack
to defeat an opponent...
But that's not where
her true strength lies.
She carries that in her soul.
[Young Masamune]
Watch closely this time, okay?
[Young Tsubaki]
'Kay.
[Young Masamune]
See.
Did you really want
to play ball, Tsubaki?
Yes!
[Tsubaki]
But I didn't...
What I really wanted
to do was play house.
I wonder how long we
could have played together if
I'd been able to tell him that.
I am Tsubaki,
a flower without fragrance...
...and when I fall...
...it will be silent and tragic.
[Masamune] What are you feeling
right now, little sister?
Do you still look down on me...?
It must be nice to have
such a sense of
superiority over others.
You just stand there,
quiet and smug,
taking care of everyone else
because you're the strong one.
How can you deny it...?
That's who you've always been.
[Black Star] Please
tell me that's not
what you're actually thinking.
You know better
than that Tsubaki.
Don't even listen to this guy.
You're wrong.
You're wrong!
You're wrong! You're wrong!
I won't take care
of you anymore...!
That's over...
I'm going to stop you!
[Tsubaki]
Please...
Feel in your soul
how serious I am!
I'm begging you.
You don't stand a chance...
No matter how brave
you pretend to be,
you're still just
a pathetic flower
with no voice or fragrance!
[Tsubaki]
You're wrong...
I won't let you call
me a pathetic flower...
I have a friend who's helped
me realize something.
He's helped me see...
...that a camellia...
does have a fragrance!
Tsubaki!
She's going inside
the Enchanted Sword...?
No, that can't be right.
Did he beat Tsubaki...?
Does that mean it's over?
[Maka]
Tsubaki!
I won't watch this...!
It can't be real!
[Black Star] Old dude...!
Let me have that stick!
[Old Man grimaces]
[Black Star]
Hey, Tsubaki!
Come outta there already...!
You haven't lost
to him, have you...?
You can put on a
better show than that!
Come back out on stage!
Encore...! Encore!
Tsubaki, encore...!
Give us an encore!
[Masamune] At last...
you've finally shown me...
What your feelings really are.
[wind blows]
[Masamune] I thought
the camellia blossom
was a boring flower...
...one without any fragrance.
But I was wrong, wasn't I...?
As soon as I touched
your soul, I realized that.
Masamune...
It's a nice fragrance.
[Tsubaki quietly weeps]
[Tsubaki]
Brother.
Encore! Encore!
Encore!
Encore... Come on... encore...!
Encore... damn it!
Give us an encore...!
We want an encore!
[explosion]
See... I came back.
Tsubaki?
I just had to pay
a visit to my brother.
You did, huh...? Welcome back...
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Are you sure
you're really okay.
Yes. I promise; I'm okay.
All right then... C'mere.
Come over here...
Black Star's giving
you a big hug.
[Black Star forces a chuckle]
I'm sorry!
[Tsubaki] Look at you,
Black Star!
You're all covered in blood...!
Are you all right?
Never mind about me,
Tsubaki. I'm fine.
[Whack]
That's it, ya little brat!
[Older woman]
Sonny!
Ryoku!
[Black Star]
The kid's still alive then...?
That's good news.
[Villager A] The Star
clan are all monsters.
[Old Man]
Beating a little kid?!
[Villager B]
Get outta here! Now!
[Black Star] You ever notice
how little dogs always feel
the need to bark loud...?
Why don't you mutts shut up?
You're scared of an enemy
that doesn't exist anymore...
How lame are you?
[Black Star] What's the point in
worrying about the past?
A real star always
keeps moving forward.
[Villager A]
Don't give us that!
[Villager B]
Go away!
[Old Man]
And don't come back!
[crowd hurls insults]
Uh oh.
Who'd wanna come
back here anyway?
I'm sorry!
Once you get to know him,
he's not bad. Really!
Even if he wasn't a
member of the Star clan,
I still wouldn't like that guy.
[Black Star]
So, Tsubaki...
Now that we're done
with the Enchanted Sword,
and you've taken care of
some baggage from your past...
...you're still gonna
be my weapon, right?
Of course!
All right!
[All]
Hey guys! Welcome back!
Thanks. What'd we miss?
I'm sorry we made
you all worry!
[Death]
Hey hey...!
Good work, you two.
Yeah, you guys were
amazing out there.
And you finally
bagged a soul, huh?
[Kid] The problem child
finally redeems himself.
[Soul] It sure took you
long enough, though.
[Black Star] I've always been
a little bit ahead of my time.
[Maka]
You did it, Tsubaki!
[Liz] That little
baby cried, you know.
[Patty] Nu-uh...!
That was you, sis!
You know, Lord Death...
I think I may have
underestimated what those
kids were capable of.
They're not so bad.
[Death] They are
still young, after all...
They've got plenty of
growing up left to do.
[Black Star]
Attention!
I hope you're all ready.
Because you're about to see
something incredibly awesome.
Oh, this should be good.
'Kay, listen to this...
Thanks to that soul we bagged,
Tsubaki's got a brand new mode!
[All]
Oohh!
Let's show 'em, Tsubaki!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
Enchanted Sword Mode...
Let's go!
[Tsubaki]
Black Star!
My soul wavelength
just got taken away.
I'm gonna miss it.
I don't think that's what
Black Star had planned...
He might not be
ready for that yet...
This is interesting, though...
Looks like Tsubaki
inherited her brother's power.
This settles it.
I was born way too soon...
The times are never able
to keep up with me.
Then we'll wait
for them together...
Right, Black Star?
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] I'm so glad that story
had a happy ending!
[Tsubaki]
Thanks Maka...!
You can have it too, you know?
[Maka]
Have what, Tsubaki?
[Tsubaki]
Happiness, of course!
In other words, this right here.
[Maka]
A jar...?
[Tsubaki] With this jar,
anyone can find true happiness.
Order today and I'll throw
in a second one free...!
Take advantage of this
limited time offer while
you've still got the chance!
[Maka]
Uh, Tsubaki...
[Tsubaki] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
Courage That Beats Out Fear...
Maka Albarn's Great Resolution?
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!
[Tsubaki] Order quickly,
while supplies last!