[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Excalibur]
Fools!
♪ opening song ♪
[Ox] In a quiet shrine nestled
in a land to the north,
sits a legendary Holy Sword
awaiting the arrival
of its next master.
The legend of this
Holy Sword extends back
through all of living memory...
It waits... sleeping silently
throughout the years.
He who draws the
Holy Sword from the ground
will be deemed a hero
and shall receive everlasting
glory and fame as a mighty king.
[battle sounds as Ox speaks] He
shall rise above all others...
Adorned with wings of light,
he shall stride
through the skies...
With a single swing he
shall cut through space itself.
He who draws the sword
is a true warrior, cutting down
all those who
stand in opposition.
But forget not,
that all of his greatness
and triumph shall be brought
about by the Holy Sword.
Forever shall the stories of
the Holy Sword's mighty
deeds be passed down...
For all eternity shall the
name of the Holy Sword
be remembered,
exalted, and honored...
The Holy Sword... Excalibur!
And now appears a brave
youth boldly seeking to create
his own place in this legendary
tale of glory and greatness.
His name?
Ox Ford!
[Maka] Legend
of the Holy Sword 2...
Wanna Go Drinking,
Gambling, and Playing?
(Ooooh!) This is the Holy Sword!
How very...
...lame.
[Excalibur]
Young lad...
How are you called?
Me...? Uh, well,
my name is Ox Ford--
[Excalibur]
Fool!
Oh, no, I'm not a fool.
You see, I'm at the top
of my class at the DWMA.
I really am quite intelligent--
[Excalibur]
Fool!
No, I'm telling you
I'm not a fool.
My legend dates back to
the twelfth century, you see.
[Ox] Oh...
[Excalibur] My
legend is quite old.
The twelfth century
was a long time ago.
Do you want to
hear my heroic tale?
Yes, of course I do.
That's why I came
here in the first--
[Excalibur]
Fool!
[Excalibur] Now then,
if you are to be my associate,
there are one thousand
provisions you must observe...
You will need to peruse these
before we begin our partnership.
[Ox] I'm sorry, but could
you tell me in what way
I'm being a fool?
Fool...! You have no
need for that information.
Oh... If you say so.
[Excalibur]
My morning always begins
with a cup of
coffee with cream...
Do you know why?
Uh, no, why do they--?
Fool!
Listen, boy...!
My morning begins with
a cup of coffee with cream.
[Excalibur] Nothing beats a cup
of herbal tea in the morning.
Thus, every morning
I begin my day with a
cup of coffee with cream.
[Ox] But you just said nothing
beats a cup of herbal--
This is the first of the
one thousand provisions.
My mornings always begin
with a cup of coffee with cream.
Don't forget it!
But... as I just pointed out,
you said nothing
beats a cup of tea--
Here... I want to
show you something.
So these people...
Er... are they your... family?
The woman
standing next to you...
Don't tell me she's your--
[Excalibur]
Of course they're my family...
Isn't it obvious...?
And a wonderful
family they were.
[Ox thinks]
Past tense?
[police sirens]
[Excalibur]
It happened long ago...
when I was still in
the flower of my youth.
[uptempo beat music]
[Excalibur]
The cities began to grow wild...
People lost hope
for the future...
They became lazy,
idle time-wasters.
[yelling and fighting]
[Excalibur]
And, to my everlasting shame...
I was no exception.
Someday...
I'll have enough money
saved to leave
this city for good.
Thus...I began to watch
the seven o'clock news
religiously every night.
I see...So that pretty girl I
saw in the picture was your---
Fool...! That has
nothing to do with it!
Uh... Then what does
it have to do with?
Honestly...!
You don't get it at all.
What am I not getting?
Number fifty-eight of the
one thousand provisions
I would like you to observe...
Never talk to me while I'm
humming to myself.
This is an important provision.
Do you understand?
Uh, I can't help but notice
that your stories and these
provisions don't really seem
connected in
any significant way--
Fool! Humming and the
nightly news share a
very tight connection indeed!
But... from what you
just told me about
your past, I thought---
A symphony cannot be
created using common sense
and probabilities!
It is already written
in the fate of the composer...!
No, that's not it...
A symphony is the inevitable
result of a bad childhood,
deafness, and too many beans
eaten after a
certain time of day.
[Ox]
Obviously.
Thus, I found myself
carrying the fate of the
entire troupe as I performed
my dance before a
capacity crowd
at the opera house.
[Ox]
Wait what?
[stage lights clicked on]
[audience claps]
[repetitive uptempo
jazz music plays]
[audience oohs and awes]
[audience applauds]
[Black Star]
Whew! I am stuffed!
[Tsubaki] This is nice.
I'm glad we decided to do it.
Getting everyone together
for no other reason than to
hang out and enjoy each
other's company.
It's peaceful, don't you think?
That may hafta change.
I can't stand out
if it's peaceful
I'll just have to shake
things up a little,
bring on a big ol' Black Star--
[Liz]
Hey Tsubaki.
[Tsubaki]
Yes... What is it?
Have you finished writing
that report we were
assigned in class last week yet?
You mean you still
haven't finished it...?
You should hurry...
Isn't it due tomorrow?
Yeah, I know...
but it is that
kind of report, so...
Oh, it's that kind, huh?
Do you think you could help me,
Tsubaki? Pretty please?
[Excalibur]
Fool!
I don't get it. I wasn't even
saying anything then.
[Ox]
Uhh... excuse me...
Mister Excalibur, sir?
Mr. Excalibur, hello!
You still alive in there?
[Excalibur]
Fool!
One must take time to think...!
Rushing forward without
considering things beforehand
is the height of foolishness.
Ah, yes, that reminds me of
another time when
I had to consider things...
That case was long ago,
but I remember it still.
[bell tolls]
[Excalibur] It was back when
I still hung my hat on
Baker Street and
called it home.
[Watson] Holmes have you
deduced anything yet?
[Holmes] Of course
I have, Watson.
It appears the perpetrator's
depravity is equal
to his stupidity,
based upon the elementary
trick he has seen
fit to employ here.
[Watson]
Elementary?!
But we're stumped.
The door was
locked from the inside.
[Excalibur]
Fool!
Precisely, Excalibur,
couldn't have said
it better myself.
Watson, you're indeed a fool.
But Holmes!
Now, Excalibur,
will you explain
to us what you see here...?
Use your impeccable logic
and great intelligence to
solve the puzzle of the
locked room and point out
the killer so we
can apprehend him.
[Excalibur]
It's quite basic, actually.
Perhaps the simplest
of tricks there is.
True, it may not seem
so simple from an
ordinary person's point of view.
Some people may even
consider it a baffling,
utterly perplexing problem.
Things will often appear
complicated
on the outside while,
in truth, they are
simplicity itself.
Of course, how one sees
these things depends
on the person.
Many people find that there
is a fine line separating the
very complex from
the very simple.
Okay, Excalibur,
I think we get your point.
Could you please just
solve the case now?
[Excalibur] Fool...!
You understand nothing.
[Watson]  Yes,
well you're spot on there.
Okay... I'm a fool.
Now please explain
the perpetrator's trick.
[Excalibur]
The trick is so elementary
that there's no
need for an explanation.
Ah?!
The killer is...
--You.
--What? Me?
[Watson cries as he is led away]
[Excalibur]
And thus...
The case was brilliantly solved.
Are you sure Watson
was really the killer?
That seems somewhat unlikely--
[Excalibur] To sum up, this
brings us to number
two hundred and seventy eight
of the one thousand provisions
you must observe...
I hate carrots...
never even think about
putting them in my food, get it?
[Ox]
Yeah I hate carrots too--
[Excalibur]
Silence!
This is number three hundred
and forty nine of the
one thousand provisions
you must observe...
Meisters should eat everything,
regardless of personal
likes and dislikes...
Never say anything as selfish
as 'I don't like carrots' again!
But that contradicts your--
[Excalibur]
Do you know what kind of
terrible tragedy such
indiscretion can lead to?
Perhaps this anecdote will
help you understand it better.
These events occurred just
after my legend began
in the twelfth century...
when I accompanied the
meister King Arthur
on an expedition to Rome.
[King Arthur] Facing an
army of this magnitude
will be arduous Excalibur.
[Excalibur] Saying such a thing
isn't like you, Arthur...
You mustn't lose heart.
[King Arthur]
Excalibur...
[Excalibur] The Knights of the
Round Table never give up.
No matter what...
You must remember that.
You swore an oath.
Of course you're right...
I've forgotten myself...
My comrades are depending on me.
[Excalibur]
We fight on for their sake.
Yes, we fight
for them Excalibur...
Will you lend
me your strength now?
[Excalibur]
Of course!
[battle cries]
And thus...My journey with
King Arthur continued on.
Your personality seemed
a lot different in that--
To sum up, that is what
led to number six hundred
and seventy nine of the
one thousand provisions
you must observe...
Always place a
dehumidifier in your room.
So... how long have you been
the kind of guy you are today?
[Excalibur] From what
I have told you thus far,
you can no doubt ascertain
that I was once a lowly,
rough-and-tumble sort of person.
[Ox] Never mind.
Forget I asked.
[Excalibur]
Listen up, everyone.
Drinks are on me today...
Drink all you want!
[girls ooh and awe]
[Girls] Excalibur!
This is so unlike you...
[Pretty Girl B]
Hey, Excalibur.
You're an incredible
man you know that?
[Excalibur]
I was all dried up.
Yes... Nothing could
satisfy me anymore.
I was but a shell of a man.
An unspeakable emptiness
grew deep inside my heart.
I became frustrated...
sad...hollow.
The gaping hole inside of me
was growing larger every day...
...slowly consuming
me from the inside out.
At least, until that day came.
[laughter]
[Pretty Girl C] Excalibur...
I'm so happy!
[laughter]
[Pretty Girl C] Excalibur!
Hurry! Come here!
[laughter]
[Pretty Girl C] I want to tell
you something Excalibur...
[laughter]
[Pretty Girl C]
I love you with all my heart!
[laughter]
[Pretty Girl C] If only every
day could be like this.
[Excalibur] You don't
need to worry about that...
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm afraid you don't understand.
The day will come when your
kindness is too great for me.
Your love will begin to
weigh me down,
and I will need my freedom.
I don't understand...
What are you
talking about Cathy?
Oh Excalibur...
Please remember this
if nothing else...
I'll always love you,
no matter what happens.
You have to remember that.
Promise me that
you will remember.
[Excalibur]
I promise you,
I will remember.
[Excalibur]
However...
...just as she had predicted...
...our time together
did not last long...
There was to be no
happily ever after for us.
Thus...
What? It ends there?!
Thus, at long last, the fighting
between the rival gangs ended.
What happened.
To sum up, this leads us
to number seven hundred
and seventy eight of the
one thousand provisions
you must observe...
Never mail a letter without
the return address and
the proper postage...
and don't call collect.
I wonder what happened
with the pretty girl.
[Excalibur] What was that
you just said, young one?
I... I said I wonder what
happened with the pretty girl.
Hmm... you wish to know
what happened next...?
As a gesture of respect
for your inquiry and interest,
I will sing you a song.
[Ox] Uhh... How does me
wanting to know what happened
make you want to sing--?
Fool!
As someone who is unaware
of the vital role that singing
has played in the
cultural history of mankind,
you are in no
position to question me...
Remember that the next time
you stop to consider
your place in this world....
You do not possess the power
to deny a singer his song.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
Uh... yeah.
Then I shall begin...
Here we go!
♪ Excalibur! ♪
♪ From the United K... ♪
♪ I'm looking for heaven... ♪
♪ I'm going to California! ♪
♪ Excalibur! ♪
♪ From the United K... ♪
♪ I'm looking for heaven... ♪
♪ I'm going to California! ♪
♪ Excalibur! ♪
[Ox]
Umm...
Excalibur!
Please... how long is this
torture going to last?
Well... I think that about
covers the one thousand
provisions that you
are required to observe.
[Ox]
Oh, the humanity...
Now, I would like for you
to participate in the
most important provision,
number four hundred
and fifty two...
...the five hour
storytelling party.
You are chosen.
[Excalibur]
It shall all be yours.
Victory and glory!
[Ox]
[Excalibur]
You shall rule the world,
reining above all others
as a mighty warrior king.
So, let us go forth together...
for victory... and for glory!
[Excalibur]
Excuse me young lad.
What is the meaning of this?
Oh, I'm sorry...
But I already have a partner,
so I really should be going now.
[Excalibur] Then why
did you come here?
Well... Funny story.
I had originally intended
to write about you for a
report I was assigned in school.
But you're lame, so forget it.
I never finished my report.
I'm gonna be in big trouble.
Hey, Black Star...
Did you finish the
report that was due today?
Yeah... I got it right here.
It's only one page. Don't
you think that's a little short.
Course it's short.
Why wouldn't it be...
There's only one
word for that thing.
So, what word did you write?
[Excalibur]
Fool!
♪ closing song ♪
[Excalibur] Attention,
meisters around the country!
I have a great
opportunity to announce.
You want to be
a warrior, don't you...?
So why not test yourself
by mastering me?
Only one person can
have this honor, so act quickly.
Observe my exquisite form...!
Notice my unparalleled
sharpness.
Act now and you'll receive
four free hours at my
five hour storytelling party!
Enter yourself in
my special drawing...!
I will be teaming up
with the winning meister...!
Don't let this
chance pass you by.
Send entries to
the address below.
May victory and glory be yours.
[All]
Lame!
[Maka]
Boy am I glad I didn't get
involved with
that Excalibur mess.
[Ox]
You're lame!
[Maka] Hey, Ox. I've been
meaning to ask you something.
[Ox] Oh...? Is it about
my stylish hairdo?
[Maka]
No, it's not that.
[Ox] Then my custom-made
glasses, perhaps?
[Maka]
Not that either!
[Ox]
What, then?!
[Maka]
Tell me...
...do you wear boxers or briefs?
[Ox]
You're lame!
[Maka] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
The Eve Party Nightmare...
And So the Curtain Rises?
[Ox]
By the way...
...I wear briefs.