A sound soul...
dwells within a sound mind...
and a sound body.
Hurry... You must hurry, Stein.
It's time to shed
your fake skin.
Give in and do
what must be done.
Look for the light.
The way out is up ahead.
Stop right there Stein.
Where do you think
you're going...?
You should be
locked in the laboratory.
That's what I'm doing:
trying to find my way back...
The fog is too thick...
and I think I've lost my way.
You have...
The madness is taking over.
I don't understand.
What're you talking about?
Haven't you
realized it yet, Stein?
I am the law's hound...
I guard this door so no one
with the taint of madness
can pass through.
You had better not
come any closer.
What's happening?
♪ opening music ♪
I wonder where everyone is.
They cancelled morning classes
since no one showed up.
That buncha cowards.
They're probably too afraid of
the madness to come outside...
I bet they're all at home right
now hiding under their beds
like babies... But
there's no need to be scared.
Not with me here... I'll tear
that Kishin apart in a second.
It'll take a whole second?
You're losing your edge.
Hi, Soul.
Yo.
You'll pee your pants
once you see the Kishin.
Oh, shut up.
Maka's not with you?
Nope, she isn't... She won't
be coming later, either.
She says she
can't concentrate...
She's too worried about Crona
and the nutty professor.
Hang in a little longer.
They let Medusa go,
didn't they...?
After that, what excuse can they
have for keeping you locked up?
Yeah... but what's going on
with Professor Stein...?
Has he come back yet?
Please tell me...
Don't you think
Professor Stein's disappearance
has something to do
with Lady Medusa?
It's possible. But you don't
need to be worried about that.
It's Professor Stein...
He's tougher than he looks...
He'll come back to us.
Call off the search? But why?
He's already left the city...
The way things are right now,
we can't afford to send
anyone else to look.
But it's so obvious what he's
doing. He's gone after Medusa.
If so, it's even
worse than we thought.
No one from the academy,
can so much as lay a finger
on that witch... Anyway,
I came to tell you we have
a Death Scythe mission for
you... Time to get it together
and come back to work.
Is that all you care about?!
You're not just a Death Scythe.
You were his partner too!
How can you give up so easily?!
He's been fighting
all this time.
Keeping the madness locked in.
Maybe he's stronger
than you think he is, Marie.
Impressive, Medusa...!
No witch has ever been able
to strike a bargain with
the Grim Reaper before.
It's so simple now...
All we do is sit and watch.
Arachne and the Reaper
will destroy each other,
and we won't have
to lift a finger.
Of course, if the plan
doesn't work... Both of them
will come looking for us...
That could get ugly real quick.
The Reaper won't break the
contract. He's too honorable.
And Arachne... Well, the
Kishin will destroy her if
the Reaper doesn't
get to her first.
We just wait a little longer
to make our move.
Where are you off to this time?
I've got a little
appointment with my lover.
Twirl 'Round and 'Roundo~ A New
World in Which The Doc Dances?
Don't cry.
If you can make it
through this anguish...
Happiness will be
waiting on the other side.
No matter how lost you feel...
There's always a way out.
Are you little girls
lost in here too?
What do mean, "girls?"
It's just me...
I'm all alone with you.
Just you and me, and that's
okay! I came here to get you.
Come with me.
We'll follow the path...
Pretty soon, it'll lead
us right out of here.
Can't you see she's a witch?
You can't stay here
forever, you know.
You have somebody waiting
for you. It's time for you
to leave this place...
but be careful of the witch...
If you let the madness take you,
you'll never find the way out.
But how do I leave?
That's easy.
All you have to do
is think about where
you're supposed to be.
Where I'm supposed to be...
Who are you, kid?
Zero reaction to magic...
It is still as a stone.
Well I could use
my wavelength to activate it.
No... there's gotta be
some trick to it.
How am I supposed to think
straight when all I have
to drink is this awful coffee?
Now look what I've done! The
coffee's spilling everywhere.
What's that?
Way to go!
This is a breakthrough!
Crafty Eibon, hiding a secret
page right in the front cover!
It's the information
we're looking for.
To activate Brew,
we have to find the key...
It's another Magic Tool.
We should send someone
out immediately...
Kid can handle
the mission easily.
We're not exactly
on the best terms right now...
I don't know
if he'll take it on.
He's still suspicious about what
we're planning with the Tools?
Too much is going on for
him to be acting like
a petulant child.
You're his father.
Tell him he doesn't
have a choice...
There's one more thing...
We need someone else.
I'd like you to call
on Uncle Bob for assistance.
Um... yeah... Who's he again?
How could you forget...?!
He's the owner of
the coffee shop nearby!
"The only coffee so delicious
it'll make you want to dance!"
Come on everybody, sing with me!
I'm falling apart at the seams
without my Mandheling
coffee beans! Oh!
Mandolin?
Mandheling, man!
I can't concentrate without
Uncle Bob's Rumba coffee...
I should have found that
secret page long before now...
If I keep going like this,
my work will continue to suffer!
Now, now, is it really that bad?
Yes...
Normally I'd never pause
to ask for outside help.
Paws?
It smells so good
I'm almost drooling!
Keep your pants on.
Lunch will be ready
in just a few more minutes.
You're calling this plate
of charred fish lunch...?
Besides isn't it Maka's turn
to cook today, anyway...?
Where is she?!
She locked herself in her room
and she refuses to come out...
She should really eat
some lunch, though...
I'm sure a bite of my yummy
fish would cheer her up.
Soul, give me a hand.
How about you be
my taste tester?
Here. Open up and say 'ahh'!
Hey, what the hell?!
How could they let
her go like that?
After everything she's done...
to Professor Stein... and Crona.
I have to stop...
If I keep thinking about it,
I'm gonna go mad too.
Mail for you.
A postcard from Mama!
The place where
I'm supposed to be, huh?
Come back here, Stein!
The laboratory?
It's a good thing I'm home
now, but I still violated
my curfew and ran off
without telling anyone...
I wonder what excuse
I should use.
Marie!
What're you doing, Marie?!
From up here...
the city looks so small.
Kind of like a prison floating
in the clouds, don't you think?
Somewhere out there...
I'm sure there's a world
that will fit you better.
Goodbye, Stein.
Marie!!
Aww... looks like she died.
But wait, isn't that
what you wanted?
You never cared about her
the way she cared about you.
Bye, Marie.
You went through
the wrong exit.
The madness has taken over
just like I thought it would.
What happened to Marie?
No need to worry.
You'll forget everything
once I'm done with you...
Everyone you knew in your old
life... even your own name.
What are you going to do to me?
You have to be punished.
You broke the law
and gave into madness.
I need to cut you open
and fix you up.
Stop it! No, don't!
So many pretty pictures!
Mama sent one to me every time
she went somewhere new.
She hasn't sent one
in a long time...
I've been kind of
worried about her.
Your mom must be
a pretty amazing lady.
A minute ago you were depressed,
but now you're all smiley!
Yeah.
So what place did she send you
a postcard from this time...?
Hey... Something's
written in the corner.
You're right... What is it?
Hey Maka.
Teaching is nothing but trouble.
I never thought I'd do it...
But look at me now...
These kids need
someone to help them...
I don't think I can quit.
But you need me too,
Stein... Don't you?
Stop it... The kids
can't see you like this.
Don't fight it, Stein.
I'm giving you the
chance to be reborn...
Let me cut you open.
Yes, a new world is waiting.
It's time for you
to shed your fake skin.
Shut up!
Shut up...! Shut up!!
This is the fruit of life.
One bite of this and all your
suffering will come to an end.
You'll feel much better.
Don't fall for it.
You were reaching
for a shadow...
An illusion you created.
You. I know you. You're me.
I know you're nervous,
but there's no reason to be...
Go on... have
a sip of your tea.
--Um... uh...
--Oh no.
Don't tell me you're
a coffee drinker, too.
I don't think I can handle any
more Tango or Rumba or whatever.
I want to make a request.
Please sir...
Please let me leave here
and go after Lady Medusa...
I wanna to try and bring
back Professor Stein!
You're still being held prisoner
for your betrayal of the DWMA...
...and you want me to trust you?
I have to go after them.
Maka's always stood up for me.
I owe her that much...
I have to do this.
Okay.
You have some things to
settle with Medusa as well...
...don't you?
Yes.
My... you've got guts,
don't you?
M-- Miss Marie!
I asked her to meet us here.
She says she wants to talk
to you about something.
I am so sorry...
This is all my fault...
I lied to you... and...
now Professor Stein's gone.
Don't apologize.
Lift up your head.
I'm not ready to hear
apologies from you yet...
Maybe someday, but not now.
As for Stein...
He's too important
to be entrusted to you.
Not alone...
That's why... I'm coming.
Just then... When I
went through that door...
I was lost for a moment.
I wasn't sure if
that's where you meant...
The place I'm supposed to be.
Weren't you satisfied
with your life?
Yes, I was... Even in a world
governed by morality,
I made it a long time
without feeling guilt.
But now...
But now what?
You finally feel guilt,
but you don't understand why.
Because instead of fulfilling
your own desires...
...you found something
more important.
You already know
the right choice.
You just have to make it.
That's why you
called me, isn't it?
Open the right door
and walk through it...
The world you seek
is waiting for you.
The world that I'm seeking...
There's always a way out.
The place I'm supposed to be.
Oh yeah!
Damn it...! You only made
that shot 'cause I let you!
Well, you'd better not go
so easy on me this time.
'Cause the person
who makes this shot...
...is the one
who beats the Kishin.
What?!
Crap.
You idiot.
Come on.
With all that's going on,
this is what they're doing?
I think it's okay... Sometimes
you have to take a break.
Not you too, Tsubaki!
Maka! Catch!
Would you quit it...?
You know I'm no good
at this game, Soul!
Here... You go play.
Thanks, Maka...
Now I'm the one
who'll beat the Kishin.
How could you betray me
like this, Tsubaki?!
Aw, you'll be okay.
Does it really matter
who beats him?
Who cares, as long as
he's destroyed... Right?
Then we can play in peace.
Don't space out on us, Maka.
Hand over the ball, little girl!
Take... Thiiiis!
Hey, it went in.
See that...? I got the ball
in just by using my head.
Uh...
So clearly, I'm the
one who's gonna pound
the Kishin into dust.
Um, I think something's
wrong with your neck.
You're playing basketball...?
Right now?
Oh, hey, Kid.
You skipped school again,
didn't you...?
What're you up to, anyway?
I came to tell you
all something.
Do you know where we got
our information about
the Kishin...? From Medusa.
They made a deal with her?
Exactly...
They released her because she
told them Asura's location.
They took a witch's
word just like that.
Even if it meant
risking students' lives.
I don't understand
what they're doing...
From now on...
We have to be careful about
who at the academy we trust.
Hurry. Hurry...
It's time to shed your fake
skin... Stop fighting it.
Just keep walking...
Don't you see that light?
You're almost there.
Is this it...? My exit?
♪ closing song ♪
What's going on...?
It's kind of like... you know...
I agree. It's very...
"you know."
So what do you know?
Oh, you know... "You know."
Oh, I know... But do you?
I definitely know.
But I don't know
if you know, you know?
I'm lost. What're we
talking about?
Um... I don't know.
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Charge Baba Yaga's Castle...!
Things are Kind of Gloomy?
Watch it... or I'll take
your soul...! You know...