[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Stein narrates]
Our battle to stop the
Kishin's revival was
drawing to a close.
Death Scythe and I wanted to
end our fight with Medusa
as quickly as possible so we
could continue on
and help the others.
But Medusa knew that
was our plan, and she did
everything she could to
draw the struggle out longer.
What?
[Stein]
Soul Force!
[Stein narrates] After I hit
Medusa with my soul wavelength,
we found ourselves
in a deadlock.
Neither of us could
take a single step.
One movement could mean death.
Meanwhile, Kid and his group
fought one last battle against
Eruka and Free in an attempt
to stop the Kishin's revival.
[Kid]
Take this!
[Free]
Eruka!
She's got the blood!
[Stein narrates] Kid and
Black Star tried to destroy
the syringe that Medusa had
filled with black blood.
Eruka was attempting to inject
the black blood into the Kishin.
[Stein narrates] At first it
appeared that Black Star had
succeeded in
shattering the syringe
that would wake the Kishin.
But unfortunately...
Black Star had
been hallucinating.
We failed?
[Stein narrates]
At that moment, Medusa let her
guard down,
and our battle ended.
And then it happened...
The Kishin awoke.
♪ opening song ♪
What is it...?
What's wrong, Maka?
An overwhelming
sense of madness...
The Kishin has revived?
[Soul]
What about the others?
I don't know...
The madness is everywhere...
I can't sense any wavelengths.
Let's hurry!
[Maka]
The Battle of the Gods...
Death City on
the Verge of Collapse?
What the...?
What's his deal?
He's scared of Eruka?
[Black Star]
Damn that's annoying.
What is it, Black Star?
[Black Star]
That thing's the Kishin?
Tsubaki...
Enchanted Sword Mode...
We're gonna kill this thing now.
[Tsubaki]
I can't...
Your body already took too
much of a beating earlier.
If we do Enchanted
Sword anymore...
...then I could easily end up
cutting off a piece
of your soul.
Shut up and do what I say!
Now hurry...!
Enchanted Sword Mode!
I can't do it!
Fine, you can
sit here and watch.
[Tsubaki]
Black Star!
Come on we're going too.
[Patty]
Kay!
[Liz]
Yeah.
Take this!
Ya creepy, naked
demon pervert...!
Black Star Big Wave!
[Black Star] My body can't even
endure my own wavelength.
You're gonna... die!
[Kid]
Black Star!
Damn it!
[Liz]
Kid!
I'm naked!
This is so wrong...!
I need to cover up.
I like the "macho look."
[impact]
Does he mean me?
[Tsubaki]
Where'd he go?
[Maka breathing
heavy as she runs]
Maka!
Come back here!
[Old Guy A]
This is great!
[Old Guy B]
Awesome!
Let's see some more!
Hot...! Hot...! Amazing...!
What a catfight!
A dream come true!
Get the hell off me.
C'mon, you're a witch,
aren't you...?
Why don't you use magic?
I will if you do...
Stupid cat!
[Human Mizune]
You're heavy...
Move already!
Oh, shut up...
You need to go back to
the sewers where you belong.
This... is too much.
[ground vibrating violently]
Hey... anyone
else feel the shaking?
Maybe you're just too excited.
No...the ground
really is shaking.
Aww... is the
poor mousy shaking...?
How pathetic.
Idiot! It's the
ground shaking, not me!
Huh...? What?
Is it an earthquake?
(Chi)... It looks like Eruka
and the others succeeded.
[Asura screams]
Look...! What's that up there?
Something came out
from underground.
That thing is Asura?
[Soul]
Maka!
[Maka weakly]
I have to...
Stop the... Kishin.
You're somethin' else...
...you know that right?
[ground vibrates]
What now...?
We've got more company?
[blast]
Whoa, what are those?
Are those...?
Death's seals are still alive...
and after all these years.
What is that... thing?
Well, at least the Kishin
left us a nice big hole...
It did make it a lot
easier to get up here.
[Eruka]
Ribbit...
Hey look!
Something's caught him.
[Free] Probably some of Death's
seals that were activated.
Will he be okay?
Those seals have been
around too long...
They won't hold a
newly-reborn Kishin.
Tore 'em apart like scrap paper.
Uh...
Never mind that now...
Free...!
Look...! there's a problem.
Hey, everyone!
What is it Eruka?
Your spell, Free...
You told us it would
last for a whole hour...
But it's wearing off
after only forty minutes!
I guess I may have exaggerated
about the time a little bit...
I'm a man, after all...
We do show off sometimes.
It's you.
Hello, Death.
[Death] Hiya...
long time no see, huh?
You doing okay...?
You look all skinny and frail...
And I know how much you
liked your heavy clothing...
You must not be very
comfortable in that outfit.
It seems you've changed too...
What's with
that ridiculous mask?
[Death] Yeah, it's kinda
different, huh?...
You see, after I stuffed
you into that bag,
I started an academy
for meisters and weapons...
My old mask would
scare the kids senseless,
so I had to make
a little change...
It was really bad.
The little ones would
even start crying!
Those seals are pretty
scary too, actually...
Everything from the
old days seems to be.
[Asura] I take it that's
also why you talk
in a funny voice now?
Yes... I've grown quite used
to all of it over the years.
Now, I'm sorry to do this
right after you've woken up...
But it's time for
you to die again.
Reaper... Chop!
[Asura laughs maniacally]
Tell me, Death.
Do you know the pain of
having all of
your skin torn off...
...ripped from
your entire body...?
I've actually forgotten
how it felt myself.
Try to make me remember!
[Death]
Ka!
Shockwaves, huh?
[Asura] My turn.
Let's see how you like this.
[gothic-like chants]
[Asura powers up]
[Asura laughs]
[Death]
Oh no!
[Asura laughs]
What is all of this...?
What's going on here.
[Sid]
What are you doing?
Split up and help
anyone who's injured.
Oh... right.
Gather all of the civillians
and lead them out of town...
You got it?
Yes, sir!
[Sid thinks] A full-scale
battle between those two could
very well blow away
all of Death City.
Lord Death...
We're counting on you.
[Death] You're not
going anywhere!
[Asura struggles]
Whoa... now that is cool.
Ha!
[Death] He hasn't reached
full strength yet...
...but I don't have
my Death Scythes...
He may be able to
strike a blow that
would finish me off for good.
[Asura laughs]
[Asura]
Outta the way!
Vajra!
[Asura]
You can't stop me now!
Lord Death, no!
[Death] You filthy,
unforgivable swine...
That's it. I'm going to
skin you alive again.
[Asura laughs]
They bounced away...?
But... how?
[Death]
You deflected my attack...
Damn you, shrewd demon.
You knew there was a
boundary past which my
attacks wouldn't
be able to hit you?
I doubt we'll ever
be meeting again.
Goodbye, master...
It's been fun.
[Sid]
Lord Death!
[Death] Sid...
our first priority is
taking care of the students
who went underground to fight.
Right.
[Death] We'll need
reinforcements...
Contact the Death Scythes
that are scattered
across the continents...
Tell them to gather...
Quickly.
Yes, sir.
[Death] To think a Kishin would
revive on today of all days...
The anniversary celebration
of the academy I built to
prevent the creation
of more Kishins.
Things are about to
get very busy.
[Eruka] We should be
safe here for now.
Who is this chick, anyway?
A combination of five Mizunes.
Oh, okay.
[Eruka] I can't sense
Medusa's magic anymore...
I guess that means
she died in there.
I just have one regret...
I didn't get to see her die.
In a way, though,
I suppose I did
kind of look up to her.
There aren't many witches
of her caliber out there.
Funny, huh?
It looks like Lord Death
and the Kishin were
fighting it out up here.
But the madness
seems to be fading.
He got away.
[Stein]
I wish I could've seen it.
If only I had stayed by
Lord Death's side like I'm
always supposed to...
...then we could have
stopped him...
Things turned out horribly...
and what's worse,
everyone'll blame me.
There's no use crying
over spilt milk, Spirit...
Besides, this isn't over yet...
If we can't figure out
a way to make this right...
we'll have a lot more
problems than your ego.
[Death Scythe]
Stein!
Damn!
I love you, you know...
... a man after my own heart.
Don't be stupid.
At your core, Medusa,
you're just like me...
You can't possibly understand
a concept like love.
What kind of woman...
...would be willing to
extinguish her own soul?
You can't imagine how
disastrous it will be...
...if the Kishin
is revived again...
Its madness will
spread like a plague.
[Death] It has been a very
long night indeed...
An exhausting, difficult night
that felt at times like
it would go on forever.
And yet...
...not all is hopeless...
Even after a night like this,
morning will eventually come.
Hot...! Hot...! Hot!
♪ closing song ♪
[Asura] A breath of fresh air
is certainly nice.
[Maka]
Hey, Mister Kishin,
it must feel good to be
outside after all this time.
What do you wanna do first?
[Asura]
Stretch.
[Maka]
What did you want to do most
while you were
sealed up in that bag?
[Asura]
Stretch.
[Maka] What did you do
for fun as a child?
[Asura]
Stretch.
[Maka]
Hobbies?
[Asura]
Stretching.
[Maka]
Special skills?
[Asura]
Stretching.
[Maka]
What's your dream?
[Asura]
To stretch.
[Maka]
How do you move a hurt person?
[Asura]
Stretcher.
[Asura] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
The Death Scythes Convene...
Stop Dad's Staff Reassignment!!?
[Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul.