[Maka] A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Crona]
Maka!
His wavelength is distorted...
It's full of bloodlust.
[Giriko] Now that
I'm good and fired up,
there'll be no stopping us!
[Giriko roars]
[Giriko] My soul's
wavelength holds
eight hundred years
of anger and hatred!
[Maka cries out]
Now Ragnarok.
[Crona]
Here we go, Maka.
[Maka]
Right.
♪ opening song ♪
[Stein] Why would the madness
wavelengths cause a
soulless creature like
a golem to go berserk?
The first golem was created
eight hundred years ago...
That's around the same time
magic weapons were
born as well.
What caused this
incident in Loof Village...?
There's only one thing
that I can think of.
The soul of the heretic
witch could be hiding
inside that old golem...
In which case it could
definitely react to the
madness wavelengths.
[Maka] 800 Years of Bloodlust...
Advent of the Heretic Witch?
[chainsaw buzzing]
Are you ready, Maka?
Yes.
Ragnarok.
[Ragnarok]
Yup!
Go Dark Sword...
Screech Alpha!
Now!
Too hard.
It may be an old golem,
but you're gonna need more
than that to bring it down...
I've taken good care of it.
[Soul]
Don't push your luck...
Back away!
[Maka]
It's okay!
I can keep going!
[Maka] I've managed to get
this close with Crona's help...
I'm not going anywhere!
[Maka gasps]
[Soul] Maka...
what's happening?
My...
My body...
Time to chop you into pieces!
[Crona struggling]
[Maka thinks]
What's happening?
Maka!
What's going on?
[Maka]
I can't move...
It's like I'm frozen.
[Soul]
What?!
Damn it... What now?
Crap...! Great. What do I do?!
What's this...?
It's thread.
Here it is!
There were mass
hallucinations in countries
surrounding the Czech Republic.
Nearly five hundred
thousand people reportedly
saw mysterious, black,
ball-like things both indoors
and outdoors in the area.
No one ever figured
out what they were...
With no other
explanation available,
the case was ultimately
considered a mass hallucination.
People who reported
hallucinations of the
mysterious black objects
described them as spider-like.
[Stein continues]
Spiders...
And the area where most
of the hallucinations
were recorded was...
It was Loof Village!
That settles it...
This wasn't a hallucination.
Eight hundred years ago,
when that heretic disappeared--
she must have split up
her body into the black
objects those people saw.
And when that was done...
she left her soul
inside the old golem.
What... was that?
Uhhhh...
A spider?
So the spiders scattered
across the world
have finally gathered.
I've waited for this.
Lord Death, it's Stein...
We need to talk.
[Death]
Hey there...! Hiya...!
How ya doin'...?
Thanks for comin'!
Good to see ya!
Well...? What's up...?
Have ya got
something figured out?
[Stein] Yes... I believe
the heretic witch
Arachne scattered her body
and left her soul inside
the golem that's gone
crazy in Loof Village.
[Death]
Arachne?
[Stein]
That's right.
It'd make sense for her
to be the first one we've
seen dramatically affected
by the madness wavelengths.
Even here, I can feel it.
The madness inside me.
Her madness is clawing its
way inside my body.
[Death] I know it's hard,
but try to endure it.
[Stein struggling]
[Stein] This is
too much for Maka
and the others to handle alone.
I'll head there
now to help them.
[Death] Now, now,
Stein, don't be hasty...
I had a bad feeling about
this situation too, you see.
Necessary measures
have already been taken.
Look. The spiders are
climbing up it.
They're being drawn into it
by the soul I sensed
in the golem.
Crona?
[Crona] Don't worry.
I'll protect you, Maka.
[Giriko]
The Kishin has been revived.
Its madness runs
throughout the world.
While you were sleeping,
the Earth suddenly became
a fantastic place to live.
Right...
Arachne?
[Crona trembles with fear]
[Bassing rap music]
[Justin]
I wonder...
Is one coffin going to
be enough for this job?
[Stein]
Arachne...
The mother of magic weapons.
This must have happened because
of the madness wavelengths.
They've stirred her
at last from her slumber.
[Death] Who knew she was still
alive after all this time?
The mother of magic weapons...
She was responsible for
bringing these creations
into the world.
She used witches' souls to
give them their ability to
transform from
people into weapons.
[Arachne breathing
heavy as she runs]
[Death] She would kill other
witches and sacrifice their
souls in order to make
her terrible weapons.
As a result...
...she found herself being
chased not only by me...
...but by her fellow
witches as well.
[Death]
Where did you go?
[Crona]
This woman... this...
...wavelength...
La--
...Lady Medusa?
It's nice to meet
you children...
I've been looking
forward to this.
Maka... Soul.
Last night you had a
little argument, didn't you...?
Over who it was
that burned the curry.
How could you
possibly know that?
It was Soul...
He forgot to turn the burner
off and scorched your dinner.
The two of you aren't
my only entertainment, though.
I've been watching everything
that's gone on
throughout the world...
For eight centuries...
...through the eyes
of my dear spiders.
You too, Crona...
The child of Medusa...
my little sister.
How delightful...
Medusa didn't love you
one little bit, did she...?
Well...
It's not too late.
I can give you my love.
[Arachne laughs softly
and slowly builds]
Oh, how delightful!
[Crona seethes]
[Ragnarok]
Go after her, Crona!
Kill the witch!
We're on fire now!
A close call...!
But I guess I have aged
a bit in these last
eight hundred years.
I'm no longer delighted...
Exterminate the brat, Giriko.
Sure thing.
No way...! He broke through
the black blood
with just one kick?
My trusty Saw Leg...
Looks like speed setting
two is enough to
take care of this brat.
I guess Medusa's research
was nothing special after all.
Cuts like that are nothing...!
I'll just harden
the black blood.
After you say, thank you!
Thank you.
You mean 'thanks very much!'
They're stronger than I thought.
I guess I'll just hafta cut 'em
in half and eat their souls.
Stop it...!
When you squat it looks
like you're going
to the bathroom.
Now we're talking!
Say goodbye, brat!
Time to die!
Nice try!
Saint Cross Knife!
[Giriko]
Who the hell're you?!
[Soul]
His arm's a guillotine?
So who won?
[Giriko]
Damn, that was close...
That guy almost got me.
It's a good thing I had my
chains ready or else
I'd be dead by now.
Quite impressive...
Who are you, anyway?
[music playing in headphones]
Too good to answer me, are you?
[Arachne]
Justin Law.
He's one of the Death Scythes.
This guy is a Death Scythe...?
You're kidding me.
Is he?
The Executioner.
He's a legend at the academy.
Four years ago, when he
was only thirteen,
he became the youngest boy
ever in academy history
to reach the level
of Death Scythe...
He did it all by himself, too...
...with no meister
partner or anything.
Oh, Lord Death...
Please grant me strength.
Attention, DWMA students...!
As there is only one opponent,
I will end this quickly...
Please wait a moment,
if you don't mind!
Damn, he's loud!
Because of the earphones, maybe?
Another weapon like me
who doesn't need a meister...?
I don't like that very much.
[Giriko] Do you have fun
sucking up to Death, boy...?
Is it worth it?
They've both got such
strong wavelengths...
They might be equals.
What is it?
A scythe...
He's the same kind
of weapon I am.
You wanna know something
that really pisses me off?
Bootlicking suck ups like you!
You're nothing but a
mongrel that Death
has housebroken!
Reverse Rotation!
Don't you even want to
hear about the heretic witch?
[Justin]
Neck Shackle Guard!
Headbutt... of Love!
You dirty bastard!
They're on such a
different level than us...!
I can't learn
anything from this.
What? Are you trying
to study right now...?!
Damn, you're a strange girl.
Now I've got
my engine running...
Why don't you take off the
damn earphones already...?
You're not listening to a
single word I'm saying,
you cocky bastard.
Huh?
I can read your lips.
I don't have to hear you...
Such a filthy mouth...
Quite shocking.
You've been reading my
lips this whole time...?
So you purposefully pretended
that you couldn't hear me...?
Now you're really
pissing me off!
[Arachne]
Giriko.
What d'ya want, lady?!
I detest children who shout.
Shouldn't you know that by now?
How can I help you, ma'am?
The golem's energy is
just about drained...
It's time for us
to begin our retreat.
Retreat?
[Arachne] Someone
is waiting for us...
But don't worry...
You'll have plenty of
opportunities to fight later.
There's no choice then...
The rest is up to you, golem...
I couldn't care less
about those brats.
They'll die soon enough.
[Justin]
Hold it!
There's no escaping!
[Golem grunts]
[Maka]
Crona!
Maka.
Lord Death's express
instructions were
to secure the academy students
and the trial student
who's with them.
Everyone, please duck down...
I'm going to take care of this.
Oh, great lord of ours
who dwells within
the city of death...
May thy name be kept true.
The prayer is increasing the
strength of his soul wavelength.
[Justin]
Oh Lord of Death...
I am your servant of peace...
I am a pillar of justice.
I am a blade of faith.
In the name of
the great Lord Death!
Law Abiding Silver Gun!
Now then...
...let us all bow
our heads in prayer.
[Soul thinks]
Amazing...
He's the same kind
of weapon I am...
...and he did all
that by himself...
With my meister
immobilized like this,
I can't even fight...
All I can do is sit
here and hold her.
Damn it.
[Soul] You still can't
move at all, Maka?
Man, that's one stubborn spell
Arachne put on you...
Doesn't look like
it's going anywhere.
I feel so inept.
Uh-huh.
Hey... hold on a sec.
Is it really necessary
to put me in here?
[All]
What?
Come on. I know at
least one of you
can read my lips.
For now I guess
our best bet is to ask
Professor Stein if he
can fix her up somehow.
Yes, I agree...
If anyone knows
what to do, it'll be him...
Stein is a doctor, after all.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm sure Stein won't
do anything weird to me.
Hey...
Maka... a flower!
Thank you Crona.
[Maka thinks] I think I
understand how Sid felt now.
A red carpet here in the
middle of the mountains?
I've been awaiting
your arrival...
Lady Arachne.
[Arachne] Mosquito. The air
here has become quite dry
and stagnant in the last
eight hundred years...
It's making me very thirsty.
I have an excellent bottle
of champagne chilled
and waiting for you.
This car's so
cramped and stuffy.
[Giriko]
There. That's better.
Humph...!
You vulgar hoodlum
show some gratitude.
What...? You want a piece
of me, old man?
Never mind your
squabbling, boys...
I'm exhausted...
Hurry to the castle.
[Death] Not only has
the Kishin revived,
but it's madness has also
revived the heretic
witch Arachne.
Yet another dangerous
enemy that must be dealt with.
[Mosquito]
It's been such a long time...
Lady Arachne this is the
network you have
spent 800 years creating.
Congratulations.
[Voices]
Lady Arachne...!
Congratulations on your revival!
[Arachne]
I will defeat you...
...Death.
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] Justin, what kind of
organization is Arachnophobia?
[Justin humming to music]
Um, Justin...? Hold on...
Can't you read lips?
Hey, Justin!
Whatever.
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Sword God Rises...
Does it Have a
Sweet or Salty Taste?
[Justin]
"Breast?!"...
How dare you speak that way?!
[Maka] I don't think you can
read my lips very well.