[Maka] A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Black Star] Fine...
he's all yours.
Be careful...
No stupid moves.
Yeah.
Gimme a shout if you
get yourself into trouble...
I'll bail you out if your
sorry butt needs saving.
Yeah, okay, I get it.
Thanks for the support.
Now go already.
Maka... Let's go!
Tsubaki, we're heading
after Kid and the others.
[Tsubaki]
Right.
I won't let you past me.
Speed Star!
Huh?!
[Black Star]
See ya! Have fun!
That's okay.
I can handle this...
People are easier to deal with
when their backs are turned.
Die, okay?
No way!
Hey, that's no fair.
[Soul]
Nice punch...!
Cutting him won't do any good
because of the black blood,
so more impact strikes
like that are what we need.
[Maka]
We have to stop him here.
We'll do a Scythe Catch
then a left rush.
His body's so hard it feels
like I'm punching lead.
[Crona moans]
[Ragnarok] Crona, quit thinking
about the brat who ran off and
focus on the one who's
right in front of you.
Round one goes to me!
[Crona]
I don't understand.
Why am I suddenly
all beat up...?
I don't know what to do.
How am I supposed to deal
with a girl who keeps
punching me like that?
[Ragnarok]
Kill her.
[Soul]
I think we can safely say
your first attack
went well enough...
But let's face it...
...you picked a fight
with the Demon Sword...
Do you have any
chance of winning?
Tell me you do.
Tell me you have a shot.
Nope, not really.
How're you so smart,
yet so stupid at
the same time, Maka?
This is awesome...
It's official: you're definitely
the coolest partner ever.
[Maka giggles]
[Soul] Well,
you'll manage somehow.
Yeah, I'll figure something out.
[Ragnarok]
Don't be an idiot, girl...
You're not gonna
'manage' anything...
Don't you remember
how this went last time...?
You and your weapon
didn't 'manage' so well.
I don't know why I
bother with you anyway...
A puny little soul like yours
is hardly even worth eating.
That star brat from earlier
looked a lot tastier than you.
You're an unappetizing,
useless little girl...
I don't even
need to fight you...
I could probably bully
you to death from here.
[Maka]
Hurray.
[Ragnarok]
Huh?
You finally see me
for who I am...
The last time we fought you
only saw me as food,
not as an opponent.
But this time is different...
This time, you're seeing
me as a person.
So I say... 'hurray'...
And as for that
meister of yours...
Why are you always
so nervous...? It's pathetic.
Leave me alone.
Why don't you understand...?
You're such a weakling...
You'll just lose again...
Why do you insist on fighting
when you know
you can't beat me.
Don't look at me like that...
That's a determined
stare you're giving me,
and I don't know
how to deal with it...
It's very unsettling.
[Maka] It may be true that I'm
physically weaker than you,
but somehow I don't
think I'm going to lose...
You see...
My soul is stronger
than yours is.
[Ragnarok]
Blabber all you want...
No one will hear your
screams when you lose.
Oh, I'm sorry...
Have I made you a bit angry...?
My name's Maka.
I'm a scythe meister...
Tell me who you are.
Demon Swordsman Crona.
I challenge you, Crona...
That's good...
You look less scared now.
Maka... so now I know the name
of the person
I'm supposed to kill.
♪ opening song ♪
[Death Scythe] Stein,
what's happening?
Against my instructions,
Maka is fighting the
Demon Sword on her own.
What?!
[Medusa laughs evilly]
[Medusa] How sad. It looks like
your precious daughter wants
to get herself killed.
I wouldn't underestimate
my daughter, Medusa.
We shall see.
[Maka] The Black Blood
Resonance Battle...
A Small Soul's Grand
Struggle Against Fear?
[Soul] Hey, Maka,
why're you giving
him time to prepare himself?
[Maka]
Well?
Here we go.
Maka get ready!
Bloody Slicer.
[Maka thinks] His hardened
blood turned back into liquid.
Bloody Needle.
This guy means business.
[Crona]
Ragnarok...
[Ragnarok]
Shut up!
Scream Resonance.
[Ragnarok screams]
Tell me...! Why are you are
you collecting innocent souls
and reviving the Kishin, Crona?
Cuz I'm always scared....
If I can get stronger
and more powerful,
I'll be able to deal
with things better...
And Lady Medusa will abandon me
if I don't become a Kishin...
If I don't get stronger,
I'll always be afraid...
Screech Alpha!
[Maka]
Bring it on...
I may be weaker than you,
but I'll take on whatever
you throw at me!
Cro-naaaa!
[explosion]
[Stein]
May I ask you something?
Where did you abduct the
child who became the
Demon Sword meister?
Your first plan was to use
the Demon Sword to create
a Kishin, wasn't it...?
But now you're more
interested in reviving the
Kishin sleeping
under the academy.
That's because your first idea
isn't working out, right...?
The Demon Sword
is failing you...
It shows no sign of becoming
a Kishin anytime soon...
...so instead you risk using
the black blood to wake Asura...
And now you're left with a
child you have no use for.
It looks like your grand
experiment has failed...
...and pretty soon,
everyone's going to know it.
[Medusa laughs]
Why the laughter...?
Did I say something
that amuses you, Medusa?
You really are
a fool, aren't you?
It may look like
I've failed to you,
Professor Stein...
...but all of my work has
pertained to the black blood
from the very beginning.
Oh, and one other thing...
...another part of your theory
that is completely wrong.
I didn't abduct the Demon Sword
meister from anywhere.
You see,
Crona is my own child.
Oh dear.
You shouldn't've gotten back up.
[Maka bellows]
Why are you still so
insistent on fighting me...?
You're never going to win.
Just give up...
I'm tired of trying
to figure out how
to deal with you.
[Maka]
He used his blood again.
Cutting attacks like that
are the wrong way to go...
The more he bleeds,
the worse off we're going to be.
Yeah, I know.
But there is one more
thing we can try.
You're right. There is that...
Let's go, Maka.
[Maka and Soul]
Soul Resonance!
[Maka and Soul power up]
C'mon... Get it in gear, Crona!
Scream Resonance!
[Ragnarok screams]
[Soul] We need to increase
our resonance rate!
[Maka bellows]
Such strong resonance energy!
So it's beginning.
Witch Hunter!
Screech Gamma!
Hey Stein,
what's going on out there?
[Stein] The black blood
is being activated.
[Maka bellows]
Figure-6 Hunter!
Letter-U Hunter!
Oh, really...?
Is that all you've got?
Uhh...
He took those hits
without even blinking.
[Soul] How can a toothpick
like him be so strong?
It isn't him, Soul...
His body itself may be weak.
But the black blood flowing
through his veins
strengthens him...
Ragnarok hardens Crona's body
so it withstands our blows.
[Crona] All right.
Now it's my turn.
Screech Gamma!
Stop it! Stop it!
Noooo! No no...
No no no noooo! No!
Stop it! Don't make
me cut your weapon now!
Hey, Soul!
No shut up...!
Maka you have to
stay out of this!
But if we keep going
at this rate, you'll--
Listen! Just forget about
that other crap, okay...?
You need to keep your
guard up right now!
Come on, Soul...
There's no point in
struggling anymore,
and you know it...
It's time to wake up
and accept the inevitable.
Let me make you stronger.
Are you hanging
in there, Soul?
Yeah.
There's something...
I think I almost have it.
[Maka thinks]
I sensed something earlier.
Like there was
no way I could lose.
It's something in Crona's
wavelength that
I can almost grasp.
If I just had more time...
No.
Are you afraid now...?
You remind me
of the little one...
I still don't know how
to deal with it either...
You have that much
in common, at least.
[Medusa]
Now... defeat it, Crona.
[Crona whimpers]
Uhh--uh I can't do it...
I don't know how to deal
with something like this now.
[Crona sniffles]
You're a bad child.
I want you out of my sight...
This is your punishment...
You'll be locked in this
room for a long, long time,
so get used to it.
[Crona] No! Please pick
another punishment.
It's too dark in here!
I can't see anything...!
You can't leave the two
of us alone. Please don't lo--
[Door closes and
the lock is turned]
[Crona crying]
It's so dark in here.
I don't know how to deal
with darkness like this.
[Ragnarok]
Dammit Crona...
Look what you did!
No, Ragnarok.
[Ragnarok]
You got me locked up in here
with you because you
couldn't pull yourself together.
That hurts! Quit it...!
You're always picking on me,
and it's not nice...
Stop twisting my nose like that.
It hurts... I can't see
anything in here,
but I know I have
a nosebleed now.
[Ragnarok] It's all your
fault, you idiot...!
Take this. And this.
[Crona] Oww...! I'm sorry, okay,
I'm sorry! Just stop it now.
--Please...!This isn't fair.
--And this and this and this...!
Leave me alone
already. Stop it!
[lock being turned]
[Medusa]
You can come out now.
[Crona]
He's so mean!
Ragnarok keeps beating me up...!
It hurts, and I don't like it...
Please make him stop hurting me.
[Medusa] Come... We're picking
up where we left off...
You will defeat
it this time, Crona.
There's no way. I can't do it...
I still don't know how to
deal with something like that.
[Medusa]
Vector Plate...
You can stay in there out
of my sight a little longer.
[door lock turned]
[Ragnarok] Damn it Crona!
You complete idiot!
--Oww. Stop it.
--Take this. And this.
--And how about this!
--You're hurting me again.
--It still isn't enough?
--Leave me alone.
--Then take this too!
--Ow ow ow! No!
[door unlocking]
How many times have
we done this now...?
And how many more times
are we going
to have to do it...?
This is getting
you nowhere, Crona.
Heh. Did you know
my blood is black?
[stabbing sound]
Bye bye... you little one.
Come on Soul...
Now is the time to act.
Maka...
You're going to die if
you don't do something...
Why not just leave it to me?
Do away with reason...
Let me make you stronger.
Not happening...!
You can give me power...
That's all.
My reason stays with me.
Oh, no.
You can't beat the
Demon Sword's
madness that way...
You're sadly mistaken if
you think reason and
discipline will give you
the power you need now...
Those aren't enough.
I've never seen anyone
have it that easy.
Understanding fear then
fighting against it...
...maintaining complete
discipline always...
Those are great powers
in their own right.
Besides, this isn't just
about me anymore...
...if we resonate any higher...
...Maka will be affected too.
Don't be an idiot,
you damn brat.
You're turning into a
pathetic whiner
all of a sudden...
What happened to all that
spirit you used to have?
Where's your drive?
Forget reason!
Just let loose and
go crazy for once!
What kind of life
can you live without a
little bit of
insanity thrown in?
Shut up!
Why are you even talking?
You're just saying
the same damn thing
over and over again.
I'm so sick of listening
to you I could puke.
You're full of crap,
and I don't listen to crap,
you got it!? Huh?
So just shut your stupid
little demon mouth
and take the lead.
I'll decide if I want to
follow you or not
how about that?!
How can I shut my
mouth and take the lead?
I dunno, just point or
something you stupid freak.
Okay, okay...
Let's just cool down
for a second here.
You and I both
want to move forward.
But it isn't going to
work this way.
We can't make progress
if we keep on yelling
at each other like this.
Right?
Yeah.
Now, I invited somebody
over to join us.
You can come in now.
Huh...? Who's there?
Now that we're all here,
perhaps we can decide
things in a more
agreeable manner.
What do you say?
Maka!
I heard most
of what's going on.
How did you get here...?
What is this some kind
of weird meeting inside
my brain or something?
[Demon]
It's simple, really...
Your souls are
resonating right now.
Is it so difficult to believe
that your minds could
be connected as well?
Alright Demon...
How do I know this
isn't just some image of
Maka you created.
Why should I trust you?
You're a very cautious
young man, aren't you...
Remember, it's your mind
we're inside of now.
You're running the show...
There's only so much
I can do in here.
Maka... Chop!
Yeah, okay... it's Maka.
Now then... Why don't we put
on some nice, relaxing music.
[Maka]
You're going to have to lead...
I'm not sure I
know how to do this.
[Soul] It's fine.
Just do whatever.
Five and six
and seven and eight...
[slinky jazz music
begins to play]
I don't understand, Maka.
What are you doing here?
Did you hear the
demon guy's voice too?
I'm not sure... Maybe...
Thinking about it...
...it is possible I heard
it faintly before...
...back when we fought
the immortal werewolf.
Yes... That would
certainly make sense.
I had entered you
too at that point.
But I was removed
shortly after I got there...
I'm still not sure how, though.
If that's really what happened,
then you shouldn't be here...
You managed to
get rid of the demon.
You might not be so lucky
the next time, you know.
Hey... when our wavelengths
are matched like this...
...you can tell what I'm
thinking... can't you, Soul?
Are you...?
You can't seriously be
thinking of using the
black blood to give yourself
the same madness Crona has!
[Maka]
I knew you'd be angry.
It's something I sensed
when I used Witch Hunter
on him earlier...
...something that I could
almost grasp, but not quite...
If I could be as
powerful as him...
Maybe I would know...
Maybe I could figure out
what I need to about Crona.
No way... It's too dangerous to
do that without knowing more...
If you do this you could
end up as crazy
as Crona forever.
[Maka]
Yeah...
I'm sorry, Soul...
I've made up my mind.
We can't be sure
you'll return to normal.
I know, but it's
worth trying, right?
All right. Fine... I give...
Do whatever crazy
things you want to.
Just remember,
no matter how far
away you end up...
I'm still your weapon,
and I will pull you back.
Oww!
[Maka]
Oh, sorry.
You really should lead, okay?
Uh-huh... I see that now.
This is more like it.
[Maka laughs insanely]
Ooooo! He flew!
I'm being pulled into
the madness with her...
Maka... I swear I will
not let go of you.
You're wrong
about that one, fool...
See I'm the one
who's leading now.
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka]
Where am I?
[Demon]
Figure it out for yourself.
[Maka]
It's dark. I can't see.
[Demon] Isn't that just because
it's night outside?
Oh...! I understand.
This is Crona's--
[Demon] Hey, stop it!
We don't want
to give away any
spoilers now do we?
[Young Maka]
Huh?
[Demon] You know, about
how you turn into a kid?
[Young Maka]
You could've told me sooner!
[Demon] On the next
episode of Soul Eater...
May My Soul Reach You
A Dry Heart Inside
Unbearable Isolation?
[Young Maka]
Watch it...
...or I'll take
your soul, mister!