[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Maka] Soul and I traveled to
Italy to collect Kishin souls
for an extracurricular lesson.
[Maka] We were able to meet
our quota for the lesson...
But just as we were
about to leave,
I sensed a troubling soul
wavelength nearby.
[door creaks]
[Maka] Something told me that
I shouldn't open that door,
but I didn't listen.
[Crona cries out]
[Crona screams]
[Maka] Inside we found a soul
who had crossed beyond
the realm of humanity.
Meister and weapon as one,
on the verge of
becoming a Kishin...
[Ragnarok screams]
[Maka] We tried
to fight them, but...
...I screwed up.
♪ opening song ♪
Soul!
Go on, Crona... Finish them.
[Maka]
Medusa the Witch...
The One Who Possesses
a Great Evil Soul?
[Medusa] Kill them and
eat their souls Crona.
I think I can deal with that.
Goobee.
Wake up... Soul, please.
[Soul]
You dumbass...
Hurry... get out of here.
[Maka]
Okay...
Soul.
Soul...
This is all my fault.
[metal colliding]
[puncture sound]
What's happening...?
How did that get there?
[collision with the door]
[Maka gasps]
[Door cracks and bursts]
Professor Stein!
[Crona cries out]
[impact]
If he's here...
...then that blade must be...
[Death Scythe thinks]
Your papa has arrived!
That's right, Maka...
Take a good look at how brave
and selfless your father is!
Professor Stein...
...is Soul all right?
The wound's very serious...
If we don't get
him treatment soon,
he might not make it.
[Death Scythe thinks]
She's not even looking at me!
I gotta say, though...
...it was an easier fight
than I'd expected.
[Ragnarok] I hardened
the blood around
your wound to
stop the bleeding.
Do I get a 'thank you'?
Yeah thank you.
[Ragnarok]
"Thank you very much"?
Are you gonna
make me hurt you?
Thank you... very much.
[Maka]
Professor Stein?
[Stein]
Hmm?
[Maka]
Who are those two?
Or what are they...?
I've never seen
anything like this.
[Stein] That is the reason
the academy was created.
The reason the
academy was created...?
So does that mean he's a Kishin?
Technically, not yet...
...but he's only one
step away from it.
[Death]
Listen to me Stein...
Take Death Scythe and
find the "Demon Sword"...
Stop it from awakening
into a Kishin.
[Stein] That is the reason
you called me back to the
academy in the first place.
I'll take care of the sword.
[Death]
We cannot allow the
Kishin to be
reborn into the world.
Do your job well, Stein...
I'm counting on you.
All right, then.
Let's take care
of this, shall we?
Yeah.
[Ragnarok] Crona,
quit standing there
staring into space
like an idiot...
If you don't get it in gear,
we're going back to
the sleep deprivation again.
No don't start waking
me up every hour again.
I don't like it!
The dark circles under
my eyes will come back!
And I don't know how
to deal with the dark circles!
[Medusa]
The Grim Reaper has sent
his greatest meister armed
with Death Scythe...
This should be a good
test to see how long
Crona can last.
[Medusa]
Crona... get them now.
[Stein] Spirit, can you stand
against the Demon Sword?
[Death Scythe]
Of course I can...!
What do you think I am?
Some kind of rusty old dagger?
Been a long time, hasn't it...?
Since we teamed up like this.
We're not as young
as we used to be,
that's for sure.
[Death Scythe]
Speak for yourself.
I haven't aged a bit.
[Ragnarok] Would you hurry up
and attack already, you idiot?!
But I've never seen a
man with a screw sticking
out of his head before!
I don't how I'm supposed
to deal with a guy like that.
[Ragnarok]
You eat him!
Swallow his soul!
[Stein]
Soul Force!
[Crona screams out]
Professor hit him with
his soul wavelength...!
Directly... This way he might
actually be able to do
some internal damage.
[Crona cries out]
[Stein]
Have another.
What?
That's the blood from
the wound we gave him.
[Ragnarok]
Bloody Needle!
Professor!
He's using every drop of
his blood as a weapon...!
But how is that even possible?
When souls are overhunted,
a Demon Sword is created...
We have to stop him
here and now...
...or he will definitely
become a Kishin...
What's more...
...the balance of power
between these two is uneven.
[Stein] The weapon's soul
is clearly dominant...
It rules over the meister's
more introverted soul,
confining it.
For the moment...
the meister still has
some strength left to fight
back against the weapon.
But if he should be
completely swallowed up,
things will get dangerous.
[Stein]
There's something else.
I see a snake
coiled around him.
What's it doing there?
[Ragnarok] If you let him hit
you with that technique again,
I'm going to stick thumbtacks
in your shoes. Got it?
No-oo...! Thumbtacks in my
shoes would stick into
my feet whenever
I tried to walk.
It would hurt,
I don't think I could
deal with that, really.
Oh, I see...
Professor Stein has a
specific fighting style.
First, he guards, using my
dad only as a shield.
Then he uses his own attack.
[Stein]
Soul Force!
[Crona cries out]
Oh, wow!
Damn, a time lag attack!
[Ragnarok]
(Goobeeyah)...
It's time to die, Screwhead.
[Maka]
Professor!
I think I'd like
to dissect you now.
[Ragnarok] (Begyaaaah!)...
screw yourself!
You won't live that long!
You ready?
Yep!
[Ragnarok]
Bloody Needle!
[Stein]
Spirit Body!
[Spirit Body] Oh dear...
I think this is too much for me!
[Ragnarok]
(Goobee)...
...let's see you
stop all of these!
[Ragnarok] Where'd the
screw-head freak go?
I don't see him...
Where the hell is he, damn it?!
[Ragnarok] Damn!
He scrambled what
little brains you have left!
Hurry up and snap out of it!
We can't afford another
hit from his soul wavelength.
There are stars and planets
floating around me...
I don't think I can
handle astronomy right now.
[Ragnarok] Astronomy's a lot
easier to deal with than death,
you moron...!
So suck it up and come
to your senses already!
Double-Palm Soul Force...!
Twin Spears!
[Ragnarok and Crona cry out]
The needles again?
No... it's over now...
I hate to say it,
but you're finished.
[Medusa]
So much for round one...
It looks like I'll have some
more experimenting to do.
[Crona screams suddenly]
[Crona and Ragnarok
scream in unison]
What's happening to him?
[Stein] He's going through
soul rejection.
[Maka] Their soul wavelengths
were united but they're
falling apart now.
[Medusa] I guess
I found his limit.
Oh well,
Soul Protect... Release.
It's another soul...
I don't know where it
came from, but I can sense it.
I feel it too...
It's a witch.
[Medusa chuckles
and then laughs]
[power surges]
A witch, huh?
Yes, and one with a
strong soul... Very powerful.
[Stein] My guess is she's the
one who put that weapon
inside the kid's body, too.
[Maka] That's the
witch's soul up there?
But how? I should have
felt a soul like that
before now...
It's incredibly strong.
[Stein]
Soul Protect.
[Maka]
What is that?
[Stein]
It's advanced magic...
Not all witches can use it.
The technique encloses the
area around the
soul with magic.
This blocks the
soul's wavelength.
The witch is camouflaged,
and her soul appears to be
that of a normal human.
So that's the soul
of a real witch...?
Mama defeated
something like that...
in order to turn
Papa into a Death Scythe?
[Medusa]
Pathetic...
Crona is such a weakling.
I'll have to punish him later.
[Medusa]
Nake Snake...
Cobra... Cobra...
Nake... Snake...
Cobra Cobra.
But before I go,
I'll punish you too.
Won't that be fun?
[Medusa]
Vector Arrows!
Let's go! Soul Resonance!
Witch Hunter!
Quite impressive.
[Medusa chuckles evilly]
[Medusa] I just dropped
by on a little errand...
Who would have thought
I'd run into the
DWMA's legendary meister?
And Death Scythe, too...!
What an unexpected pleasure.
I would love to stay and play
with you kids a little longer.
But I'm afraid I can't...
Perhaps we can
all play another time.
[Death Scythe]
Hold it, lady!
[Stein]
No... It's okay.
Let's leave her for now...
I'm more worried about Soul.
[Maka thinks]
Soul.
Papa.
[Death Scythe]
Come on...
Let's go home, Maka.
[bells tolling]
[Death]
Interesting...
Those two had a
pretty rough time, it seems...
How is Soul holding up?
[Death Scythe]
Stein is operating on him now...
He was hurt pretty bad,
but I think he'll be all right.
[Death] The Demon
Sword has surfaced...
And it's united
with a meister...
..actually embedded within him,
from what you say...
And behind it all
is a powerful witch.
Hmm...
[Death]
Goodness! It looks like
things are getting pretty
crazy around here,
aren't they?
[Death Scythe] Uh...
Lord Death...
Don't you think you
might be taking this
a little too lightly?
[Death]
Oh?
[Girl A] How was your
extra credit lesson?
[Girl B] All in all, it went
pretty well, I guess.
[Girl C] Ugh... You're lucky.
I have a remedial
lesson tomorrow.
[Girl A] Personally I'd rather
have a remedial lesson.
Didn't you hear...?
Apparently a one-star kid
named Soul Eater got injured
and had to be
brought back for surgery.
[Girl C] You're kidding!
I hope he's all right!
What? Something
happened to Soul?
Professor Stein?
Have you been waiting
out here this whole time...?
Why didn't you go take
a nap or eat or something?
I need to know
how Soul is!
[Stein]
Uhh...
The operation was a
complete success.
Once he rests up a little bit,
he'll be as good as new!
He's okay!
Thank you so much, Professor!
[Maka]
Umm...
Would it be all right if I went
in to check on him now?
Sure... That'll be fine.
Thank you!
[Death Scythe] That's a nice
fake  smile you're wearing.
[Death Scythe]  So tell me what
you wouldn't tell Maka...
What is Soul's condition really?
[Stein] The wound itself is
all right after surgery.
That much I can say, at least.
But, there is still
something that bothers me.
[Death Scythe]
Go on.
[Stein] I'm not exactly certain,
but it might be a curse.
A curse...?
What kind of curse is it...?
Will he be all right?
The Demon Sword,
Ragnarok has black blood...
Some of it appears to
have gotten mixed
into Soul's blood...
I can't say for sure
how it will affect him,
but I doubt it will be good.
[Maka thinks]
Soul.
Back away...
I won't let you
touch my meister...
[Maka thinks with a shaky
internal voice] I'm sorry.
I am your weapon
partner, Maka...
That means I am always
prepared to die for my meister.
[Maka]
You did it all for me.
Just you wait...!
I'm gonna become as
strong as you are, Soul...
I promise I am.
[impact]
Soul! Soul...!
Are you okay?!
It's going to be all right!
Black Star is here for you now!
Open your eyes!
One look at my big,
handsome face and
you'll be cured for sure!
Black Star no!
[Tsubaki]
Sorry about that, Maka.
Maka?
[Medusa]
Oh my goodness...
What happened to the door?
[Medusa] From the looks of it,
things have been lively in here.
[Maka]
Dr. Medusa...
Good afternoon.
Hey, Doc. What's up?
Are you here to check
on how Soul's doing?
Um, well...Miss Maka...
Yes...What is it?
Can you do me a favor and
help me out with your father...?
I can't get him off my leg.
[Death Scythe]
Oh, my darling!
My dear, white-coated angel!
Please heal me!
My heart is in need
of your sweet,
sweet medical loving!
Only you can cure--
Soul had a difficult
lesson, didn't he...?
He was in pretty bad shape.
Yes... I'm sorry...
It's all my fault
that he was hurt.
[Medusa]
But he's okay now.
And as for you...
This will only make
you stronger, Maka.
Yeah!
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] He who draws the Holy
Sword from the ground will be
deemed a hero and shall
receive everlasting
glory and fame...
He shall rise above
all others, a mighty king...
Adorned with wings of light,
he shall stride
through the skies...
With a single swing he shall
cut through space itself...
The legendary sword,
more powerful than
any other, old as time itself...
The Holy Sword Excalibur!
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Legend of the Holy Sword...
Kid and Black Star's
Great Adventure?
Watch it...
Or I'll take your soul.