[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[crackling of fire]
[Death] Hey, Sid... are you
going to be all right?
[Sid]
Yes... I'm sorry.
I... I should've tried to help
you escape too, Lord Death...
...but the distance
was too great...
No. No excuses...
I have failed you.
[Death]
No no. You made the best
decision given
the circumstances.
Still, I can't believe it.
Our own doctor Medusa...
Was a witch this whole time.
She was using Soul Protect...
It's the only way she
could have hidden from us.
[Kilik]
Lord Death.
Aren't there any techniques
we can use to combat
the Soul Protect move?
[Death]
Kilik...
[Kilik] If not, then we're
basically helpless...
How can you fight
what you can't see?
[Death] Our struggle
against witches
has been going on
for centuries.
Over the years, witches have
come up with an
number of new spells.
But for every new spell meisters
and weapons have developed
new ways of countering them.
For instance,
in order to detect
and hunt down witches,
meisters were born who
had the ability to sense souls.
But now the witches can
counter them by
using Soul Protect...
So what we have to do
now is develop a new technique.
The only way to do
that now is to Kishinize.
[Kilik]
What?
[Death] I suppose there's no
point in hiding it anymore.
If you shut the lid on
something that stinks,
all you're really doing
is hiding the bad smell.
To get rid of it, you have to
open the lid back
up and dive in.
Heya, everyone...
Could I have your
attention for a moment?
There's a Kishin sleeping
underneath the DWMA.
[silence]
[Sid] Uh... I think they may
need more than that.
♪ opening song ♪
[Death] It all happened before
this academy was created.
I'll begin at the beginning.
This is the story of a man...
His name was Ah-shura.
Asura kept himself covered,
wrapping his face
in long scarves
and layering five shirts
on top of each other...
He wasn't very good at
trusting other people...
He didn't confide in anybody.
He was basically a big ball
of paranoia wrapped up
in a dozen scarves.
Tell me what happened
with the eastern witches.
Sir, by the time we arrived...
Asura had slaughtered them all.
Asura was a member
of my personal squad.
He was by far the best
and strongest of all
the Eight Guardians.
However, he was also the
most frightened one
of them all...
...always terrified
of something.
Asura became
obsessed with power...
Eventually, he broke our most
sacred rule and began
collecting the souls of humans.
And thus, because of him...
...it was born.
The Kishin.
The source of all madness.
Hold on. I thought only
weapons could consume souls...
How was Ashura able to eat them?
I told you he was
a frightened man...
He was terrified of
his partner as well.
So... He ate his own weapon...
What?...
How is something
like that even possible?
[Death] You know...
Now that I think
about it I'm not sure he was
ever human to begin with.
It's possible he's nothing
more than the embodiment of
something that lies
deep within his heart.
Fear, for example.
The Underground
Battle Commences...
Break Through
Medusa's Vector Arrow?
[Maka]
Hey, Kid...
How did Lord Death seal away
this AH-shura guy
in the first place?
[Kid] My father
tore off Asura's skin,
made a tightly
sealed bag out of it,
and stuffed Asura inside...
Then he rooted his own soul
and body here inside Death City
to keep the Kishin
from ever breaking free.
[Black Star]
And because of that
Lord Death can
never leave the city?
[Maka] What if
the seal was broken,
and the Kishin
managed to get free...?
Would Lord Death be able
to go wherever he wanted?
[Stein]
That wouldn't work.
Lord Death has attached
his soul to this town...
I suppose you could even say
he's become one with Death City.
So it's like he's
trapped inside himself.
[Stein] If he wanted
to go somewhere...
He'd have to find a
way of giving the city legs...
And I don't really see that
happening anytime soon, do you?
[Death]
(uh-uh)
[Stein] You can't
even imagine how
disastrous things will
be if the Kishin is revived.
Its madness is like a plague.
[record skipping]
Oh, Soul...
...you should know
you can't control it...
Hell is something you
carry around with you.
Right inside your weak,
flimsy little head.
Now, come along...
Madness is waiting for you.
There's no escape...
You're like a needle stuck
in the grooves of a record,
spinning around and around.
Yeah right. Screw that.
Your analogy isn't persuasive...
I mean look at that needle.
It's jumping around
all over the place.
I'm waiting for your decision.
What's it gonna be, Soul?
[panicked voices]
[roaring fire and explosions]
[Blair meowing in
a sing-song style]
The city sure is lively.
They really know
how to throw a party...
I wanted to go too,
but they said only
academy students
were allowed at their
fancy gala... No fair!
I don't have a job,
so I don't have any
money to go shopping.
There's no choice...
I'll just have to go
visit Fish Shop Guy.
He knows me, so he'll
give me something at least.
[fire crackling]
[Fish Guy]
Blair... is that you?
Hi, Fish Shop Guy!
Blair... Here you go.
I saved this fish just for you.
Oh no! Fish Shop Guy...
Who would do
something like this?
[incoming rocket-type sound]
[Blair]
What's that?
They're responsible.
Hold it... Right there!
[Blair] It took me forever to
find that free source of food.
[Mizunes make
"chi-chi-chi" sounds]
I'll have to take care
of those cheeky rats.
[Black Star] We've gone
a pretty long way now.
Hey, Maka, can you sense any
witches up ahead with
that little gift of yours?
[Maka] Their Soul Protects are
probably on right now.
Oh... all right...
That's lame...
Sensing stuff's is the only
thing you're half decent at.
[Maka] You really know
how to piss me off.
What... what...?
Professor Stein!
Yeah.
I've got something...
It's a soul just
beyond those shadows.
There's someone there.
I know that soul...
I'm sure of it...
That nasty,
despicable feeling...
...Papa!
I'm not nasty... or despicable.
How did you manage to escape
from the trap they set up there?
When it comes to chasing a
woman no one's faster than I am.
I shoulda guessed...
...it is a relief to
see you, though...
I wasn't sure how much I'd
be able to do without
my weapon around.
What do we got...
Are they up ahead?
Uh-huh...
...lying in wait for us.
Listen up...
From this point forward,
there's no telling
what could happen...
It'd be best for you weapons
not to return to human
form during the battle.
When you're vulnerable a single
blow could be the end of you.
Right!
--Uh... okay.
--Yeah!
[Black Star] Why're they sitting
up there waiting for us...?
I thought they were on
their way to the Kishin.
No. They would've
left some behind for protection.
[Black Star] Hey did
you hear something?
Hear what?
[footsteps]
Yeah, I heard that.
It sounds like footsteps to me.
[Black Star[ So they're finally
showing themselves...
Who's it gonna be?
[Stein] Someone able
to defend against
and defeat multiple
opponents...
Someone who can attack
several people simultaneously...
Someone who will make
absolutely sure not to
let us through, no matter what.
How lovely to see you all again.
[Stein] All right, here's how I
think it's going to break down.
For the most part,
we can anticipate
our enemies' moves...
The first roadblock is
going to be Medusa.
The Demon Sword
will be the second barrier.
After that,
the remaining two will
be making their
way to the Kishin.
The werewolf Maka
and the others fought
before is immortal...
...so he'll be in
charge of protecting
the black blood at all costs.
Now then,
this is what we will do.
I'll stay here and
keep Medusa busy.
While I'm distracting her,
I want the three of you to run
past her as quickly as possible.
Kid, you're the most mobile
of our little army,
so you continue on ahead of us
after the two who are
heading for the Kishin.
Understood.
Black Star, you'll be keeping
the Demon Sword busy
so Kid and Maka can get through.
Since you can attack directly
with your soul wavelength,
you can do the most
damage to the Demon Sword.
Yeah!
Finally, Maka...
You run on past Medusa and
the Demon Sword to
catch up with Kid...
Then you destroy
the black blood.
[Maka]
Right.
[Stein] There's just
one last thing...
I want you all to
make me a promise.
I want you to
promise not to die.
Can you do that?
--Uh-huh.
--Yes sir!
Holding a strategy meeting
right in front of your enemy...?
Is that really the best idea?
Ah, well...
I guess we'll just have
to take our chances, won't we?
[Medusa] Always so
stupidly confident...
...aren't you?
Shall we start the party then?
Nake... snake...
cobra... cobra...
Nake... snake... cobra... cobra.
Here we go.
Don't worry about getting
past her right away.
Wait for a good opening
to present itself...
Stay calm and collected.
Here goes.
[Medusa]
Vector Arrow!
Times... three!
She's picked a perfect spell
for keeping
multiple attackers at bay...
And it's more
powerful than last time.
If you get scared,
go to sleep.
[Liz]
Yeah, okay.
I'm not gonna hold back!
Now...! Enchanted Sword Mode!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
[Black Star bellows]
It's time to punish you...
Impudent boy!
[Kid]
Death Slide!
We're through!
Maka...! Black Star!
I'm going to keep moving!
Tsubaki!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
[Black Star bellows]
Why, you...!
Yahoo!
Two of them made it through.
Enchanted Sword Mode off.
We've got somewhere to be.
[Soul] Maka...! Hurry up
and go after them.
Yeah.
All vectors to Maka!
[Maka thinks]
I remember this...
I've seen how this spell
works once before.
So I already know the
path that I have to take.
Right down the middle.
[Stein thinks]
The vector arrows radiate
from their power
source, Medusa...
If Maka is going to get
past them, her best bet is
to go through
the gap in between.
But in that position,
she'll be surrounded
by the arrows...
A moment of hesitation,
and she could die.
And if Maka doesn't get
there before
the arrows close in,
she won't have a chance.
Focus on your speed, Maka.
[Maka]
I have to run faster!
Think you can't be afraid
of what you can't see, huh?
[Maka thinks]
The arrows sound close.
Maka!
[Maka thinks] Damn it... Of
course I'm imagining the worst!
And now the fear is beginning
to weigh down my legs.
No...! The fear should
make me run faster!
Faster!
You aren't going to beat me!
You aren't going
anywhere, girl! Nice try!
[Stein]
Soul Force!
It's just you and
me now, Medusa.
Good! Let's keep going.
[Soul]
Yeah.
[Medusa]
I miscalculated...
To think that I let all
three of them get away.
But as long as I stop you
from getting any further,
my plan will still succeed...
Those three are just children.
They should be taken
care of quickly enough.
[Stein] I wouldn't
underestimate those children.
Didn't you learn anything
about our students' abilities
during your little
stint at the academy...?
Or are you just a fool?
No, I think you're the fool.
We'll see... I wonder how
they're going to do
against the Demon Sword.
[Kid bellows]
[Crona]
Huh?
[Ragnarok] Hey, did something
with four wheels, two legs,
and two arms just blow past us?
Hmm.
[Death Scythe] Medusa...
I must admit I always
loved seeing you
in your nurse's outfit.
Although the thought of
seeing you out of it
was more exciting,
especially if
I was taking it off.
You know I was
dancing with her tonight,.
Yeah, I saw that.
Just rub it in, why don'tcha!
[Medusa chuckles]
Boys, boys, must you fight...?
It embarrasses me so.
Does it...? How impolite of us.
[Medusa] My, my... That's quite
a large soul you have...
Perhaps I would be willing
to dance with you again.
Thanks, but I'm gonna
pass on that one...
I don't think you're
really fit for dancing now.
My feet...! What is this?
Those are Soul-thread Sutures...
The soul wavelength I blasted
into you a second
ago is still there...
As we speak it's working its
way through your body
like an electric charge.
I used the wavelength like
a thread to sew your
feet to the ground.
How can you control your
soul wavelength that precisely?
A weapon can have
more than one use.
He doesn't just amplify
a meister's wavelength...
It's also possible
to increase the
accuracy of wavelength control.
So then it's a technique that
only powerful meisters and
weapons can pull off.
Medusa...
Listen closely to
what I have to say.
I'm the only Death
Scythe at the DWMA.
If I allow the Kishin to
revive under my watch,
I won't be able to show my
face to any of the other
Death Scythes around the world.
[Medusa]
Your point?
The point I'm making...
The point he's making
here is that we're going to
beat you no matter what, right?
Hey...! Not cool, Stein...
That was my big line!
Medusa...
Consider yourself fired.
Now!
Sutures, go!
[Stein]
It's over!
You're not going to get any
closer to me
than that, Professor.
Vector Plate!
What did you do?
[Medusa] Anything that's on top
of one of my vector plates will
be sent flying in the
direction the arrow is pointing.
Of course, the plates work on me
as easily as they do on you.
Vector Plate!
As you can imagine,
I'm not eager to fight
you up close anymore.
Damn! Not again!
Now... come back this way.
Sutures.
You sewed your own body
to keep yourself in place!
But...How can you fight this
when you're all sewed up...?
Light Serpent!
Removal.
Good one! You timed that just
right so you could use
the plate to your advantage.
[Medusa]
Vector Storm!
[Death Scythe]
Stein!
I have a thousand snakes inside
me that are under my control...
They won't let any
easy prey like you escape.
"Not eager to
fight me up close."
Yeah, right.
When you cause pain,
you love to see it up close...
Masquerading as a school nurse
was just another
one of your charades.
You're nothing but a liar.
I'm afraid you're
wrong about that.
"Why don't you join me?"
You remember that, don't you...?
While we were dancing?
I really meant what
I said at the party...
I'm not lying when
I say that I want you...
You're a scientist
just as I am...
We could watch the
world progress together.
What do you say,
Franken Stein...?
Think about my offer...
I'm not asking
you as an instructor...
...but as a man of science.
[Death Scythe] Hey...
what's wrong, Stein?
Vector Plate.
[Medusa] Don't you see,
Professor Stein...
The vector plates around
you all point to me.
There's no point in resisting.
I always get what
I want in the end.
There is no escaping from me.
[Crona]
This isn't good...
We let someone get through
without even fighting.
We're going to
get in trouble again...
I can't deal with that.
[Black Star]
Are you the Demon Sword?
You don't look like you can
put up a very
good fight to me...
Defeating you isn't gonna
enhance my reputation at all.
Seriously, dude,
you look pretty messed up.
Are you okay?
Oh well, who cares about you
and your problems anyway...
The important thing is that
I'm gonna kick your ass.
[Tsubaki]
Be careful Black Star.
Black Star. Hold up a second!
[Black Star] You made it here
quick for someone so slow.
[Maka thinks]
The sword.
Stand back and
let me handle this.
What? Why?
What are you doing, Maka...?
That's not the plan.
Professor Stein
wanted Black Star
to take care of the
Demon Sword, remember?
Listen to her, she's right.
Our attacks don't work
against that thing.
What're you thinking...?
I'm not gonna let you
take the spotlight off me.
Come on now. Keep acting cocky
like this and you're
gonna get yourself killed.
[Maka thinks] This is my
chance for revenge.
A good student like you, Maka?
Disobeying a direct order
from a professor?
What...? Teen rebellion?
Just stand back.
[Black Star] Alright, if that's
how you're gonna be...
Spotlight's yours.
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka[
It's time for revenge...!
Let's go, Soul.
[Kid] Hey, what're
you talking about...?
I'm Kid, not Soul.
[Maka]
Don't worry...
We're going make him pay
for what he did to you, Soul.
[Kid]
Didn't you hear me?
I'm not Soul!
[Maka]
I will get stronger!
[Kid]
Nope, still not Soul.
[Maka] Are you ready
to do this, Soul?
[Kid]
I'm...! not...!Soul!
[Maka] On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
The Black Blood
Resonance Battle...
A Small Soul's Grand
Struggle Against Fear?
Watch it...
or I'll take your Soul.
[Kid] I'm telling you,
I'm not Kid!
Wait, no...that's not right...