[Maka]
A sound soul...
...dwells within a sound mind...
...and a sound body.
[Tsubaki] The camellia blossom,
also known as 'tsubaki,'
is a flower without fragrance...
It proclaims nothing,
blooming in silence...
When the blossom's
petals scatter,
it is quietly tragic.
Hey, Tsubaki...
...what do you
feel like playing?
I wanna play ball...
I am Tsubaki...
A silent flower
without fragrance.
♪ opening song ♪
[Death] The Enchanted
Sword Masamune...
If he continues like
this for much longer,
he will become a Kishin.
Are you sure you're
ready for this, Tsubaki...?
You know how difficult
a battle it's going to be.
I'll stop Masamune...
Difficult or not,
I can do it.
[Death] What does Black Star
have to say about it?
I haven't told him everything,
if that's what you mean...
He doesn't need to
know the whole story yet...
But he said he's willing
to put his soul in my
hands for this battle.
[Death]
Did he?
You've got yourself a
good partner there, don't you?
Yes!
[Maka] The Enchanted
Sword Masamune.
~Break the Soul Possession:
A Heart Sings in the Rain?~
[Maka] Huh... I wonder what
Professor Stein is up to,
cancelling class like this.
Think he's skipping so
he can dissect something?
There's no telling
with that guy...
...but don't worry about it...
Today'll be cool...
especially without Captain Spaz.
I'm guessing you
mean Black Star?
Hey, Tsubaki
isn't here either.
[Girl Student A] Oh, Maka
haven't you heard?
Huh...? Heard what?
It's all over school.
Someone overheard the
teachers talking
in the faculty room earlier.
[Girl Student B] Apparently
Black Star and Tsubaki
went off to collect the soul of
the Enchanted Sword Masamune.
Enchanted Sword?
I hope they're okay.
[Maka thinks]
It's gonna be tough...
They say the sword is
on the verge of
becoming a Kishin.
[Vulture screeches]
So, uh... where are we?
[Tsubaki]
This is Shin...
...also known as the
village of needles.
[Black Star] Why do you
think a little out-of-the-way
village like this would
become a target for
the Enchanted Sword?
[Tsubaki]
I'm not sure.
Frightened souls seem
to be more likely to
become the Enchanted
Sword's targets.
Maybe the villagers
are afraid of something.
Black Star, there's
something I need to tell you...
It's about the
Enchanted Sword...
I haven't exactly
explained everything yet...
Whoa... What's that?!
[Tsubaki]
Black Star!
Yahoo...! Black Star on stage!
Front and center. Yeah!
[Tsubaki] Please try
not to break that.
A big star's here to
perform in your tiny village.
Come on out, everybody!
Quiet down, Black Star!
[Old Man]
Hey, kid!
Just what do you think
you're doing up there?
Do you realize you're
standing on top
of the village's
guardian deity?
Yeah, geezer...?! Confess!
You're the Enchanted
Sword, aren't you?
Black Star!
So you're targeting
the old folk first...?
You young city
dwellers are horrible!
Black Star, it's not
right to attack the elderly.
What was that, young lady?!
Elderly? I'm still as
active as ever.
All day and all night.
[Black Star] There,
you see that...?
He's definitely the
Enchanted Sword.
[Tsubaki] He's definitely not
the Enchanted Sword.
[Ryoku]
What's going on...?
You come to
visit the old timer?
The Enchanted Sword. It's you!
Huh?
It isn't that boy, either!
My, what've we here?
Friends of Ryoku's
come to visit?
All right. Then it's
this lady here!
Quit it, Black Star!
It's not her either!
That's a very
troubled young boy.
[Black Star] Everyone here
looks like a suspect...!
You know what that means:
[Black Star] I'm gonna have
to take 'em all down!
[Ryoku] What do you
want with our village?
You've come here
to kill more people,
haven't you?!
[Old Man gasps in fear]
I know that tattoo
on your shoulder...!
You're a member of
the Star Clan.
Don't lie to us, boy!
What did you say?
[Villager B]
The Star clan?
[Villager C]
Did he really say that?
[Villager B] What the hell
are you doing here?
[Villager C]
You murderer!
Money?
From what I've heard,
all you Star clan members
will do anything for money...!
So why don't you take
that and get out of our village?
[Crowd murmurs in agreement]
Okay... this village too huh?
[Older Woman yells
as she lifts a boulder]
[Black Star]
Uh-oh!
[Villagers yell]
Go Away... Get Out...
Tell your friends
to stay away too...
[Black Star] Damn. On top of
everything else, it's raining.
Finding this stupid
Enchanted Sword would
be a lot easier if I could
see souls like Maka.
But I can't, so I'm just gonna
have to rely on my
other five senses to
track the thing down.
Unfortunately, those other
senses aren't quite as
sharp in a downpour.
What happened back there...
you wanna know, don't you?
[Tsubaki] No... that's not
what I was thinking.
[Black Star]
It's a real long story...
I'm not a big fan
of long stories.
Right... I get it.
If you'd rather
not tell me, that's okay.
It's happened before,
remember?
It was another old man,
a lot like the
one this time...
He saw my tattoo
and started freaking out.
I know.
The tattoo is a symbol
of my family, the Star Clan.
[Thunder]
[Black Star] They were a
clan of assassins...
Everybody knew that
they would do
anything for money.
[stabbing sound and screaming]
[Black Star] After a while,
killing people wasn't enough...
They were hungry for
even more power...
...so they began
hunting human souls.
But now it's just me...
I'm the last member
of the Star clan.
[Tsubaki]
I didn't know.
What happened to the
rest of your clan?
[Black Star] Thirteen years
ago, their souls were taken
by Lord Death and the
meisters from the academy.
At the time I was
still just a baby,
so they didn't
take my soul...
That's when the
school took me in.
That's it... The end.
But is it though...?
You don't resent the
academy for what they did?
[Black Star] Nah,
this was all way back when...
So long ago that I wasn't
even close to being
the big star I am now.
It was a simple case
of cause and effect...
My old man and old lady
crossed a line
they shouldn't have...
...and they paid for it
by having their
souls taken away...
That's all there is to it.
Yeah, I guess...
...but I still don't like
to see people treating
you so badly for it...
It wasn't your fault.
Come on, are you
kidding me...?
All because of my name,
I was the center of
attention earlier! Yahoo!
Remember a little while ago...
...when I said I had
something I needed to tell you?
[Black Star] You don't have to
tell me until you're ready.
I don't know how
you're connected
to the Enchanted Sword...
...but he's an enemy we
have to defeat, isn't he?
That's all I need
to know to fight him...
Take some time to get
whatever's inside you settled.
And then you can tell me
everything you need to tell.
[Tsubaki]
Okay.
[Black Star] The rain's
starting to come down harder.
[thunder clap]
[Masamune]
I could stand here thinking...
Or go sleep... or play...
Or...
Eat!
[thunder clap]
[Maka]
Lord Death!
I wanna know why you
sent them after Masamune?
[Death] Whoa!
Easy there, meister...!
Who invited you to the
Death Room in the first place?
[Maka] The one hundred
and eighteenth rule in
the Death Weapon Meister
Academy handbook states:
In the event of an emergency,
students are allowed to
enter the Death Room without
first obtaining permission."
[Death]
Really...? It does?
[Kid] What type of enemy is
this Enchanted Sword, father?
[Death] Kid, you've come
to join the party?
The Enchanted Sword guy's
not like the Demon
Sword guy, is he?
I hope not.
The Enchanted Sword doesn't
have a witch with him...
He might actually be
less dangerous if he was
under a witch's supervision.
The Enchanted Sword takes
advantage of the
fear in people's hearts...
He uses that fear in order to
take possession of
his targets...
And gain control
of their bodies.
He then consumes
his victims' souls...
Unless someone stops him...
He will become a Kishin.
[thunder clap]
[Ryoku] How could that
Star clan murderer
dare to show up here?!
Will this sickle do
any good against
someone like him?
I'm old enough now to
get revenge for what they did...
It was those assassins who
killed my mother and father.
[Masamune]
You see, I think...
And therefore, I am.
And therefore, I eat.
Hey, who are you?
[Masamune]
I think, therefore I eat...
You have fear hiding
in your soul, don't you?
Fear? What would make
you think that?
No, I don't have any fear.
We'll see now, won't we?
With my power...
Your fear could
disappear for good...
Gone, just like that...
What do you say?
[thunder clap]
[rain pouring down]
[Old Man] Ah, Ryoku... so this
is where you've been hiding.
I brought some stuff
we can use as weapons if
that assassin comes back.
Thirteen years ago we
put up those needles...
In all that time we haven't
had a single thief come along...
Not that you have
anything to worry about.
I'll protect the village
like I did in the old days...
I'm still just as spry
as I used to be.
No one can take me.
[Old Man] That's an
interesting sword you got...
What's a fancy old weapon
like that doing in here?
Ryoku... are you okay?
[Old Man screams]
It's him!
Let's go!
Right!
No... wait Ryoku...
what's gotten into you?
[Masamune] Ryoku...?
Who is this Ryoku...?
I am the Enchanted
Sword Masamune.
I think, therefore
I am hungry... for souls!
[Old Man groans with fear]
[Black Star]
Ya--hoo!
You're the Enchanted Sword, huh?
Wait a sec...
You're the bratty
kid from earlier,
the one with the money.
What the hell's happening here?
It's the Soul Possession
technique...
Just one thing that
sword can do.
I've never heard
of that before...
How's it supposed to work?
[Tsubaki] You know how normal
meisters, and weapons match
each other's soul wavelengths
to unify themselves...?
The Enchanted Sword
doesn't do that...
Instead of matching,
he simply takes over
a person's soul and
controls their body.
And when he's finished,
the host's soul is devoured.
[Tsubaki]
That's the Enchanted Sword...
Its blade was so
beautiful once,
but now that beauty
is clouded by darkness.
[Masamune]
Oh, it's you, is it?
Tsubaki...what now?
He may be powerful but
he can't control two soul
wavelengths at one time.
Listen, Black Star...
If you shoot your soul
wavelength directly
into that boy,
the Enchanted Sword will be
forced to separate from him.
After that,
leave the rest up to me.
Just shoot my
soul wavelength at 'em.
That's all you
want me to do?
[Tsubaki]
Yes.
I joined the academy in
order to hunt down
the Enchanted Sword.
This is my fight.
And I'm sorry...
...to put you in the
middle, Black Star.
Tsubaki...
Come on. Please tell me
that isn't what you're
actually thinking...
You know better
than that don't you?
Weapons and meisters... depend
on each other, don't we?
[Black Star] You can
lean on me, Tsubaki...
And you can do it a
heck of a lot more
than you do now, got it?
Yes.
Puppet Shadow.
[Tsubaki]
Black Star!
What the hell was that?
[Shadow] Shadow...
shadow... shadow!
[Black Star] You gotta
be kidding me...!
The Enchanted Sword can
even control a possessed
person's shadow?!
[Shadow]
Shadow!
[Masamune]
Get him, puppet!
So it's two against one, huh?
Let's shake this thing, Tsubaki!
Ninja sword mode.
[Tsubaki]
Right!
Speed Star!
[Black Star]
Ha! You missed...!
I'm too fast.
You can't catch me!
Yahoo...!
Can't see me, can you...?
Nope, I bet you can't...!
And do you know why...?
Because I'm one dude
who's way ahead of his time...
You'll be lucky to even
see one hair on my head...!
Blink for just one second,
and you'll miss me...
That's how fast I am...! Yah--
[Tsubaki]
I think you may want to
save Speed Star for days
when it isn't raining.
I'm just a dude who's
way ahead of
his time, you know...
Does that mean
I was born too early,
because time can't
keep up with me...?
Man, Speed Star...
is way deep, huh?
[Shadow]
Shadow!
Ow! Ow...!
It's all I can do
to avoid his attacks...
I don't have any time to
hit him with one of my own!
I have to do something!
Playtime's over...
Now we fight for real.
[Tsubaki]
That stance!
Careful, Black Star...!
He's going to shoot
a beam from the sword.
Now die.
Puppet Thrust!
[Black Star]
I see it.
[Black Star thinks]
Blocked!
Branch out, shadow!
[Shadow]
Sha-dow!
[Black Star thinks]
I'm not done with you, not yet.
[Shadow]
Shadow!
[Black Star thinks] Damn...!
I'm still ahead...
It's not my time yet.
[Black Star thinks]
Come on...
Is it my time now?
Tsubaki...! Kusarigama!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
Now?
[Black Star]
Now!
Here we go, Tsubaki!
Okay!
[Black Star and Tsubaki]
Let's go! Soul Resonance!
[Black Star]
Shield Star!
[Tsubaki] I'll do
anything to defeat you.
You dive relentlessly
into destruction without
considering what lies ahead.
And now Black Star has you!
Puppet!
[Shadow]
Shadow!
Your time is finished now!
Mid-air combat is
something I'm good at.
Which makes this...
my time!
Now, Tsubaki!
[Tsubaki]
Right!
[Tsubaki thinks]
Black Star... Thank you.
I'll be back.
Oh, interesting...
I see... You're planning to
come inside, aren't you?
[Tsubaki thinks] From this point
forward, it really is my fight.
I will bring down
the Enchanted Sword.
[Tsubaki screams]
[Soul]
What just happened?
[Stein] Tsubaki's gone inside
the Enchanted Sword.
Why would you do that,
Tsubaki...?
We have to stop this somehow!
What is she thinking?
How is a weapon supposed
to fight without her meister?
[Death]
You don't get it.
The fight is taking
place inside their souls...
Anything could happen now.
It had to come to this...
You see... Tsubaki is the only
one who can stand
against the Enchanted Sword.
[thunder clap]
[Black Star]
Tsubaki...
You're in, make sure
you come back.
[Tsubaki] This is the
inside of the sword.
[Tsubaki]
Where are you?
[Tsubaki] I know what
you're going to do...
You'll come after my soul...
You'll try to possess it.
[Masamune]
Soul Possession...?
No... not that.
I think I'll devour your
soul just the way it is.
[Masamune]
It's so nice to see you...
...Tsubaki.
Hi, brother.
[Both]
Ready?
♪ closing song ♪
[Maka] Hey, Soul!
The preview's already started!
[Soul] Uh-oh! We don't
have much time left...!
What should I say...?
I can't think of anything!
[Maka] Well, hurry up. We only
have fifteen seconds left.
[Soul] I dunno.
I'm all choked up...
I've barely said anything
until this preview.
[Maka]
You're useless.
On the next episode
of Soul Eater...
Tsubaki, the Camellia Blossom...
What Lies Beyond the Grief?~
Watch it...
...or I'll take your soul!
[Soul] Just don't
take my screen time!