- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ DOGFIGHT ♪
- ♪ BACKFIRE ♪
- ♪ YOU'RE BIG TIME GAMBLER ♪
- ♪ BREAK IT, BREAK IT
STRIKE IT, SHAKE IT ♪
♪ BABY, THIS IS YOUR ECSTASY ♪
- ( car engine revving )
- ( tires squealing )
- Takumi: I'VE FINISHED
ALL THE DELIVERIES, DAD.
- Bunta: AH, GOOD JOB.
- OH, ONE THING, I DECIDED
TO GO AHEAD AND KNOCK OUT
ALL THE DELIVERIES TOMORROW AND
THE DAY AFTER THAT, IF IT'S OK.
- OH, THAT RIGHT? I THOUGHT YOU
AND I DECIDED TO TAKE TURNS
DOING THE DELIVERIES?
- WELL, YEAH, WE DID,
BUT MY TEAM'S GOT AN
AWAY MATCH NEXT WEEK,
SO I'M DOING THIS TO COVER,
YOU KNOW, WHILE I'M GONE.
- SO, GUESS THINGS
ARE CHANGING AROUND HERE.
NOW YOU'RE
CALLING ALL THE SHOTS.
IT USED TO BE THAT
YOU'D JUST COMPLAIN.
NOW YOU LIKE
MAKING DELIVERIES?
- IT'S NOT THAT IT'S A "GOOD
TIME" OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
BUT IF I DON'T DRIVE AKINA, I
START TO GET A LITTLE NERVOUS.
WHEN I'M AWAY FROM HOME,
I'M DRIVING ON ALL OF THESE
STRANGE COURSES,
PLACES I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
AND I'M ALWAYS TOO FOCUSED
ON BREAKING THEIR RECORDS.
I DON'T GET A CHANCE TO
CONSIDER ANYTHING ELSE.
I NEVER THOUGHT OF
IT LIKE THIS BEFORE,
BUT I'M RELAXED ON AKINA.
SOMETHING ABOUT THE WHOLE
PLACE PUTS ME AT EASE,
BECAUSE OF THAT,
I BEGIN TO NOTICE OTHER THINGS.
SEE, IT'S NOT THAT I HAVEN'T
MASTERED THE EIGHT-SIX, BUT IF
I'M GONNA TRY OUT NEW THINGS,
I WANNA DO IT HERE, I GUESS THAT
JUST MAKES THE
MOST SENSE TO ME.
TRY THE NEW STUFF ON AKINA
WHERE I'M COMFORTABLE.
I WON'T SAY SOMETHING
STUPID LIKE
"I WANT TO MAKE THE
DELIVERIES EVERY DAY",
BUT I THINK I'D LIKE TO DO
THEM AS OFTEN AS I CAN.
- IMPRESSIVE, KID, YOU'RE
ALREADY STARTING TO PUT TOGETHER
THE IMPORTANCE
OF A HOME COURSE.
- Itsuki: WELCOME!
- CHECK IT OUT.
- HEY...
- IT'S OUR OLD PAL.
- SHOWING YOUR FACE
AROUND HERE,
AND OUT IN BROAD DAYLIGHT, TOO.
- TODAY'S MY ONLY DAY OFF
FROM WORK,
I DIDN'T HAVE A
WHOLE LOT GOING ON
SO I THOUGHT I'D SWING BY HERE.
- NOW LISTEN TO ME,
HAVING NOTHING TO DO
ON A DAY OFF
CAN BE A MIGHTY BIG A
PROBLEM FOR A KID LIKE YOU,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM YOUR
GIRLFRIEND LATELY?
- YEAH. YOU TALKED NATSUKI MUCH
SINCE SHE LEFT TOWN FOR TOKYO?
YOU NEVER SAY.
- GOT A LETTER
FROM HER IN APRIL.
IT SOUNDED LIKE SHE
WAS HAVING A GOOD TIME.
KNOWING HER, I'M SURE
SHE'S ADAPTED JUST FINE.
I MEAN, THAT KINDA THING
IS HER STRONG SUIT.
IT ALWAYS HAS BEEN.
- WHY DON'T YOU GET OFF YOUR
BUTT AND VISIT HER SOMETIME?
- OH, NO, SHUT UP!
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT.
HE'LL DROP EVERYTHING HE'S DOING
AND GO RUNNING AFTER HER IF
YOU GIVE HIM PERMISSION.
- COME ON, GUYS, I WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO GO ANYWAY.
I'M TOO BUSY. I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO BE RUNNING OUT OF TOWN.
- YOU WHAT?
- I ALREADY GOT ENOUGH
ON MY MIND TO WORRY ABOUT
WITH THE TEAM AND MY JOB
AND ALL OF THAT STUFF.
I DON'T HAVE ROOM TO THINK ABOUT
ANYTHING ELSE. MY PLATE'S FULL.
- I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BUT IF YOU'RE GONNA KEEP SAYING
THINGS LIKE THAT, THEN...
- YOU'LL JUST BE
KENJI THE SEQUEL.
- YEAH, AND YOU WON'T GET ANY
SYMPATHY FROM US WHEN YOU ARE.
- BETTER BELIEVE IT,
THE GUY'S GETTING OLD, MAN,
AND NOT A GIRLFRIEND IN SIGHT.
- YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY
LIVING THIS LONELY OF A LIFE,
JUST SWINGING BY THE GAS STATION
EVERY TIME YOUR DAY GETS
A LITTLE BORING?
- YOU TWO ARE THE LAST
PEOPLE ON EARTH
WHO SHOULD BE SPITTING
OUT CRAP LIKE THAT!
- Itsuki: KENJI!
- I SHOULD APOLOGIZE, I MEAN,
LIVING SUCH AN OFFENSIVE AND
LONELY LIFE WITH NO GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT JERKS. BEEN HEARING
A LOT ABOUT YOU TAKUMI.
THAT PROJECT D YOU'RE WITH
IS ROCKING OUT.
I SAW THE POSTING
OF YOUR LAST MATCH.
GAVE ME CHILLS.
SERIOUSLY, MAN, NICE WORK.
- NOWADAYS, TAKUMI
ALONG WITH KEISUKE TAKAHASHI
ARE THE TWIN STARS REPRESENTING
OUR FAIR GUNMA AREA.
THEY'RE ALMOST
LIKE SUPERHEROES.
- YOU GUYS ARE TOO GOOD.
WE'RE ALL REALLY IMPRESSED.
AREN'T BOTH OF YOU, LIKE,
INVINCIBLE NO MATTER
WHERE YOU GO?
- IT'S NOT LIKE EVERY WIN IS
EFFORTLESS. SEEMS LIKE EVERY
ONE IS BY THE SKIN OF OUR TEETH.
AND WHO KNOWS HOW TOUGH
THE NEXT SET OF GUYS WILL BE?
THAT'S THE PROBLEM THAT WE HAVE
TO FACE DOWN WEEK AFTER WEEK.
IT'S ACTUALLY KINDA
NERVE-WRACKING.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
THE PRESSURE IT CAN PUT ON YOU.
- SO DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHO YOU'RE GONNA RACE NEXT?
OR DO THEY NOT
TELL YOU THAT STUFF?
- NO. THEY TELL ME.
THEY'RE CALLED THE TOUDOU.
I THINK
IT'S THE TOUDOU SCHOOL... .
- WHAT? YOU'RE RACING
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL?
- ARE THEY A BIG DEAL? WELL?
- YEAH. I'VE BEEN HEARING
ABOUT THEM FOR A LONG TIME NOW.
IT'S A TRAINING SCHOOL
FOR DRIVING TECHNIQUES.
THAT'S RUN BY A CAR SHOP OWNER
AND EX-RALLY DRIVER.
STARTED WITH ALL HIS YOUNG
CAR-LOVING CUSTOMERS,
THEN IT JUST
EXPLODED FROM THERE.
- IT'S A TRAINING SCHOOL
JUST FOR DRIVING TECHNIQUES?
IT'S EVEN KNOW
A THING LIKE THAT EXISTED.
- MMM-HMM. WHAT I HEAR IS
IT'S A GROUP OF STUBBORN RACERS
WHO ARE MORE INTERESTED
IN SPEED.
IT'S ALL THEY WANT.
THEY COULD CARE LESS ABOUT THAT
DRIFTING STYLE
THAT SEEMS TO BE SO
POPULAR WITH ALL YOU KIDS.
A LOT OF THOSE TOUDOU SCHOOL
ALUMS HAVE GONE PRO. AND WORD ON
THE STREET IS THAT PLENTY OF THE
GRADUATES ON THEIR TEAM
ARE ALREADY AT
SEMI-PRO STATUS.
- WHOA. NOT THE GROUP I'D
WANT TO BE GOING UP AGAINST.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
- ( car tires squealing )
- TOUDOU, WHAT'S UP?
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
I HEARD THAT YOU NEEDED
TO TALK TO ME...
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HEAR THERE'S AN OUTSIDE
TEAM COMING IN.
YOU PLANNING ON RACING
AGAINST 'EM, HUH?
- YEAH, PROJECT D.
I WAS HOPING TO.
- ALRIGHT. FOLLOW ME.
- TOUDOU, THIS CAR, IT'S...
- IT'S A DEMO MY SHOP USES.
DIDN'T KNOW IF YOU WANTED
IT FOR THE RACE.
- I APPRECIATE YOUR OFFER.
BUT, I THINK IT'S BETTER IF
I USE MY OWN CAR.
I MEAN, THE TOUDOU
COMPANY'S DEMO CAR
IS AN OVERWHELMING MONSTER.
I JUST DON'T THINK IT
WOULD BE MUCH OF A COMPETITION
IF I DROVE IT OUT THERE.
I WIN THE RACE IN THIS, I
WOULDN'T FEEL LIKE I'D DONE IT
WITH MY OWN SET OF SKILLS.
- C'MON, DON'T BE
SUCH A NAIVE KID!
LOOK, I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE SO
HARSH WITH YA. I JUST FIGURED
YOU'D TRY TO SAY SOMETHING
STUPID LIKE THAT.
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER. JUST
DO THINGS THE WAY YOU THINK THEY
SHOULD BE DONE. THE RACE IS
ONLY FOR FUN ANYWAY, RIGHT?
HEY, JUST DO YOUR BEST, OKAY?
IF I FEEL LIKE IT, MAYBE I'LL
DROP BY AND CHECK IT OUT.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU DAIKI?
YOU'RE GONNA TURN DOWN
THAT OFFER? WHAT A WASTE.
IF IT WAS ME,
I'D ACCEPT WHAT THE CHIEF
DIRECTOR THROWS OUT THERE,
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
- MAN, THIS CAR IS BEYOND
YOUR WILDEST DREAMS.
SERIOUSLY, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF YOU'D BE ABLE TO HANDLE IT.
- LOOK, I GET IT, SAKAI. YOU
CAN LET IT GO. I JUST THINK
USING YOUR OWN CAR IS A RULE
THAT PEOPLE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HONOR ON THEIR OWN.
BESIDES MY EK'S BEEN TUNED-UP TO
THE POINT THAT THERE'S NO CHANCE
I'D LOSE TO
ANYONE IN A DOWNHILL.
- HEY, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TRY TO RELAX ALREADY, DUDE?
I'VE HEARD OF PROJECT D TOO,
BUT WE HAVE BEEN TRAINED BY
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL,
YOU KNOW? THESE SUCKERS
ARE PROBABLY SO WEAK WE'LL BE
DISAPPOINTED OVER IT FOR
THE NEXT MONTH ANYWAY.
- YEAH, I GUESS MAYBE YOU'RE
RIGHT, SAKAI, BUT I MEAN...
COME ON, DON'T THEY, PISS YOU
OFF EVEN A LITTLE BIT?
THE ALMIGHTY PROJECT D...
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
THE INTERNET OR HOMEPAGES...
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE ALL
THEIR POSTS ABOUT THEIR
ACCOMPLISHMENTS ARE
JUST PLAIN BRAGGING.
IT'S OBVIOUS THESE GUYS
ARE FULL OF THEMSELVES.
- YEAH, YOUR RIGHT...
- NOTHING GETS UNDER
MY SKIN MORE THAN PEOPLE
WITH ATTITUDES LIKE THAT.
I WANT TO SHOW THOSE PUNKS
THAT THE WORLD
IS FULL OF FAST DRIVERS.
THEY'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONES WHO CAN DO THIS.
- OF COURSE NOT. AND WITH THIS
EK NINE HERE, I'M SURE YOU'LL
HAVE NO PROBLEM SHOWING THEM
AS MANY TIMES AS YOU WANT...
- I'M GONNA.
- Fumihiro: RYOSUKE. I'VE BEEN
MEANING TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS FOR A WHILE...
WELL IT'S ABOUT THE HOMEPAGE WE
SET UP. DON'T YOU THINK MAYBE
IT'S JUST A LITTLE
TOO PROVOCATIVE?
- NO IT'S FINE.
- THAT'S JUST THE WAY
WE WANT IT TO BE.
IT'S IMPORTANT WE'RE PERCEIVED
AS THE BAD GUYS.
WE WANT TO BE HATED BY THE
PEOPLE THAT WE'RE CHALLENGING.
- BUT IF WE DO ALL THAT...
- YES. OUR OPPONENTS WILL
GET ALL WORKED UP
AND GO AT US WITH EVERYTHING
THAT THEY'VE GOT.
THE TOUGHER THEY ARE THE
BETTER IT'LL BE FOR US.
IF OUR BACK'S NOT AGAINST THE
WALL, THEN THE BATTLE WON'T BE A
HARD ONE AND THERE'S NO POINT
TO IT. YOU KNOW THAT WINNING
BATTLES AND SETTING NEW COURSE
RECORDS ARE SOME OF PROJECT D'S
OBJECTIVES BUT THAT'S NOT ALL
THIS TEAM'S ABOUT.
FROM THE VERY MOMENT I STARTED
THIS WHOLE THING, I'VE HAD A
DIFFERENT PURPOSE IN MIND FOR
IT. THERE'S ANOTHER MEANING
HIDDEN WITHIN THE
"D" IN OUR NAME.
SOMETHING THAT NO ONE
KNOWS ABOUT BUT ME.
- HEY, HOLD ON A SECOND, MAN,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU EVER TALKED
TO ME ABOUT ANY OF THIS?
- IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
DON'T TAKE IT THAT WAY.
I HAVEN'T EXPLAINED
IT TO ANYONE YET.
AND I DON'T PLAN
TO FOR A WHILE.
- QUIT BEING SO
SECRETIVE RYOSUKE.
C'MON TELL ME WHAT'S UP.
WHAT DOES THE D STAND FOR
IN OUR TEAM'S NAME?
- YOU'LL FIND OUT EVENTUALLY
FUMIHIRO, LIKE EVERYONE.
- YEAH, BUT WHEN WILL
"EVENTUALLY" BE?
- Ryosuke: AROUND THE TIME
THE PROJECT IS COMPLETE.
- Fumihiro: THEY SAID THEY'LL
WITHDRAW THE LOCAL CARS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
BUT IT'S LIKE THE COURSE
HAS BEEN RENTED OUT TO US.
- IT MIGHT SEEM LIKE THAT BUT WE
STILL HAVE REGULAR TRAFFIC
TO WORRY ABOUT DON'T WE?
- NO. THE ROAD'S STILL UNDER
CONSTRUCTION SO IT WON'T BE OPEN
TO REGULAR TRAFFIC FOR A WHILE.
APPARENTLY WE SHOULD
BE FREE AND CLEAR.
THE ONLY CARS ON THE
WHOLE MOUNTAIN
SHOULD BE OURS AND THEIRS.
- UNDER CONSTRUCTION...
- SO THAT'S WHY.
WHEN I SAW IT ON VIDEOTAPE
IT WAS AN AMAZING COURSE...
THERE ARE A WHOLE LOT
OF SHIFTS IN ELEVATION.
AND THE ROAD WINDS
AROUND QUITE A BIT.
IT MIGHT BE FRESHLY PAVED AND
WIDE ENOUGH FOR US TO DO THIS,
BUT THERE'RE PLENTY OF FALLEN
ROCKS SCATTERED AROUND.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW
YOU LOOK AT IT,
YOU COULDN'T SAY THIS ROAD HAS
A CLEAN SURFACE.
- KEISUKE!
- OH, YOU. WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE BACK AT HOME.
- YOU DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE I CAME
ALONG? BUT, I'M THE DRIVER
FOR VAN TWO THIS TIME.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD AT LEAST
KNOW WHO YOU WERE WORKING WITH.
LOOK, KEISUKE...
ONCE YOU'RE DONE GEARING UP YOUR
CAR, COULD YOU PLEASE TAKE ME
FOR ONE RIDE SHOTGUN. JUST ONE.
I REALLY NEED IT.
I JUST WANNA LEARN MORE
BY WATCHING YOUR DRIVING
TECHNIQUE UP CLOSE.
I REALLY THINK IT'LL HELP.
- I DON'T KNOW KID.
DOUBT WE'LL HAVE ENOUGH TIME
BEFORE THIS WHOLE SONG AND
DANCE GEARS UP.
- THIS RACE IS REALLY GONNA BE
TRICKY. I NEED TO CONCENTRATE.
- ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT IT?
- KENTA, OPEN YOUR EYES.
HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED ANYTHING?
- ALRIGHT, WE'RE ALL SET.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE READY
TO ROLL, KEISUKE.
- COOL.
- WE SHOULD GO, TOO.
- OKAY.
♪ HEY! I WANNA CALL YOU
AGAIN AND AGAIN ♪
♪ WITH YOUR VOICE YOU
CARRY ME ON THE SAND ♪
♪ WHERE MY PAIN HAS
GONE SO CLOSE TO THE WAVES ♪
♪ I DON'T WANNA DRESS ME
FOR MASKIN' MYSELF ♪
♪ INTO MY MIND
INTO MY BRAIN ♪
♪ HEART'S ON FIRE FAR AWAY I
HAVE A DREAM TO SPEND WITH YOU ♪
♪ LISTEN TO ME
RIGHT FROM MY HEART ♪
- Fumihiro: THEY'RE SO LAID BACK
IT'S STARTING TO CREEP ME OUT.
THIS WHOLE THING ABOUT LETTING
US HAVE TOTAL RUN OF THE COURSE,
LIKE THEY'RE NOT EVEN CONCERNED.
EVEN I'M BEGINNING TO
FEEL THE PRESSURE
STARTING TO
BUILD UP AGAINST US.
I WANNA KNOW HOW THESE TOUDOU
SCHOOL PEOPLE DRIVE.
- Ryosuke: YOU SHOULD HAVE
A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
HOW THEY DRIVE IF I TELL
YOU KYOICHI SUDO
OF "THE EMPERORS"
USED TO BE ONE OF THEM.
THEIR WHOLE TEAM IS TOUGH
TALKING VETS, JUST LIKE HIM.
- IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF GUYS
JUST AS GOOD AS KYOICHI?
LOOK, WE DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS,
RYOSUKE. I MEAN PROJECT D
DOESN'T EXACTLY HAVE A LOT OF
RACES UNDER ITS BELT YET.
MAYBE WE SHOULD PUT THIS ONE ON
HOLD AND RACE THEM LATER?
- NO. IF WE CAN BE DEFEATED BY A
TEAM LIKE THIS, THEN THERE'S
NOT A CHANCE WE'LL EVER SURVIVE
THOSE FUTURE BATTLES.
WE'LL FIGURE OUT OUR TRUE
WORTH HERE, ON THIS RUN,
IN THIS BATTLE.
BY THE END, WE'LL HAVE
CRUSHED THE TODO SCHOOL
INTO THE ASPHALT.
- PROJECT D. THEY WERE WAY
MORE TOGETHER THAN I EXPECTED,
GOTTA GIVE 'EM THAT.
- HONESTLY, I WAS IMPRESSED.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T SAY IT.
BUT YEAH, EVEN THE COMPOSITION
OF THEIR TEAM MADE SENSE.
- YEAH, GOOD POINT.
THEY BROUGHT THREE VANS FULL
OF PARTS AND TIRES.
I GOTTA ADMIT, THAT'S A
PRETTY SMART MOVE.
- BOTH THE FD AND THE EIGHT-SIX
EACH HAD THEIR OWN PERSONAL
MECHANICS AND THOSE GUYS WORKED
FAST, MAN. I MEAN REALLY FAST...
THOSE DUDES HAD SOME SERIOUS
SKILLS IF YOU ASKED ME...
- IT'S GOTTA BE A
PRETTY CLEVER GUY
PULLING ALL THESE GREASE
MONKEY'S STRINGS.
- EVERYTHING I'VE SEEN SO FAR
TELLS ME THESE DRIVERS COULD BE
BETTER THAN WE THOUGHT. UNTIL
YESTERDAY I WASN'T EXPECTING
MUCH MORE THAN THEM SHOWING UP
AND LOOKING SCARED.
- WELL, I'M JUST LOOKING FORWARD
TO RACING ANOTHER TEAM
FOR A CHANGE.
IT'S ALWAYS TOO COMPETITIVE
WHEN WE RACE EACH OTHER ANYWAY.
IT KINDA SUCKS ALL THE FUN
RIGHT OUT OF THE WHOLE THING.
- NOT TO MENTION,
CHIEF TOUDOU'S ALWAYS ON
OUR CASES FOR EVERYTHING.
CAN'T MAKE ANY
MISTAKES. YOU STOP PAYING
ATTENTION FOR ONE SECOND AND
HE'S THERE TO SCREAM AT YOU.
- YEAH. AND COMPARED TO OUR
RACES AGAINST EACH OTHER, THE
ONE TOMORROW NIGHT'LL BE A PIECE
OF FREAKIN' CAKE. KINDA MAKES
ME WISH I WAS OUT THERE RACING.
SO WHY DON'T I JUST DO THAT?
- YEAH, ME TOO. I WANNA RACE!
- GIMME A BREAK, YOU GUYS.
DON'TCHA THINK YOU'RE A BIT
OUTTA THEIR LEAGUE?
I THINK IT WOULD BE BEST IF ALL
THE GRADUATE DRIVERS SAT THIS
ONE OUT. AND WE SHOULD LEAVE
IT TO THE CURRENT STUDENTS IN
THE INTEREST OF
FAIRNESS TO BOTH TEAMS.
DAIKI'S EK WILL RACE DOWNHILL.
AND MY INTEGRA TURBO WILL
TAKE THE UPHILL.
- WELL, I GUESS THAT'S
THE WAY IT IS...
- BUT IF YOU TWO LOSE, WE'RE
NEVER GONNA LET YOU FORGET IT.
YOU'LL BE DISHONORING THE NAME
OF THE TOUDOU SCHOOL.
AND YOU'LL BE DISHONORING US.
- YEAH. AND IF YOU LOSE,
WE'RE GONNA PENALIZE YOU,
WITH LIKE A MILLION YEN.
WHAT'DDAYA THINK ABOUT THAT?
- WAIT, A MILLION YEN?
- THAT SOUNDS PRETTY ROUGH.
- IF THIS IS A JOKE,
IT'S NOT FUNNY, YOU GUYS.
- ( all laughing )
- ( car engine echoing )
- OIL PRESSURE'S STABLE. HOW
ARE THE TIRES WORKIN' OUT THERE?
- THEY'RE HOLDING TIGHT TO THE
ROAD. I CAN REALLY LET HER OUT.
I'M GONNA TAKE FIVE, THEN I'LL
RUN THE COURSE TWO OR THREE MORE
TIMES WITH THESE SETTINGS.
AFTER THAT, I'M DONE.
- SURE.
- YOU KNOW, THIS ROAD TWISTS
AND TURNS LIKE A GRAPEVINE.
THAT DOWNHILL IS GONNA
BE ONE INTENSE RIDE.
- I CHANGED THE BRAKE
PADS YOU HAD
TO MORE DURABLE ONES.
IT'LL COST YOU A BIT OF CONTROL
AT FIRST, SO KEEP THAT IN MIND.
I DON'T WANT YOU
SLIPPING OUT THERE OK?
- THANKS, MATSUMOTO. TIME TO SEE
WHAT THIS COURSE HAS TO OFFER.
- BRING HER BACK AFTER
ABOUT FIVE RUNS.
I WANT TO CHECK ON THOSE
PADS AND MAKE SURE THEY'RE
NOT GETTING STICKY ON YOU.
- OKAY.
- RYOSUKE LOOKS DIFFERENT.
BUT SO DOES EVERYONE ELSE.
WHAT IS THIS FEELING THAT'S
HANGING OVER EVERYTHING?
I NEVER FELT ANYTHING LIKE THIS
DURING THE RED SUN'S
EXPEDITION BATTLES.
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING AMAZING
IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN HERE.
I'M GETTING NERVOUS.
I ALMOST WANT TO RUN AWAY.
- I WONDER IF THE FIRST STEP TO
BEING A DRIVER FOR PROJECT D IS
BEING ABLE TO WITHSTAND
THIS KIND OF TENSION.
- IKETANI! ITSUKI!
THE BIG RACE IS TONIGHT!
PROJECT D'S GONNA TAKE ON
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL!
- WOW. YOU REALLY
DON'T HAVE A LIFE, DO YOU?
- DUDE. DOESN'T THIS GET YOU
EXCITED? AREN'T YOU EVEN THE
SLIGHTEST BIT CURIOUS ABOUT
HOW TAKUMI'S GONNA DO?
- SURE. BUT I'M NOT
SHUTTING DOWN MY LIFE
AND HAULING TO TOCHIGI
JUST TO WATCH A RACE.
- HEY, WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
WATCH IT BY YOURSELF, KENJI?
NOT LIKE YOU HAVE
ANYTHING ELSE TO DO.
- ENOUGH! QUIT TALKING ABOUT
HOW I HAVE NO GIRLFRIEND,
YOU GOT IT?
- I NEVER MENTIONED IF YOU
HAD A GIRLFRIEND OR NOT,
YOU FREAKIN' PSYCHOPATH.
GIMME A BREAK ALREADY!
- Kenji: YOU JUST SAID IT!
I HEARD YOU!
- Iketani: YOU HEARD THE
VOICES IN YOUR HEAD!
- SO TONIGHT THE NIGHT. BUT
THESE GUYS FROM THE SCHOOL
MIGHT BE TOUGHER THAN WE THINK.
- Fumihiro: FINALLY, LOOKS
LIKE THE SUN'S SETTING.
I SLEPT LIKE HELL LAST NIGHT.
THE DAY FELT LIKE IT LASTED
A YEAR. I WONDER WHY THE
ATMOSPHERE AROUND
HERE IS SO STIFLING...
I GUESS MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE I
DIDN'T SEE ANY OF THE LOCAL
DRIVERS ON THAT COURSE LAST
NIGHT, NOT ONE TIME.
IT'S LIKE THEY DIDN'T CARE.
IT BOTHERS ME NOT BEING
ABLE TO SEE WHAT MY
OPPONENT IS MADE OF.
- WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
DIG UP ANY DATA ON 'EM.
- Fumihiro: YEAH, EXACTLY.
THEY HAVEN'T BOTHERED TO
CHECK UP ON HOW WE
DRIVE EITHER. THAT GIVES ME A
BAD FEELING ABOUT THIS, OR WHO
KNOWS, MAYBE I'M
THINKING TOO MUCH.
- AT ANY RATE, THIS JUST
SHOWS HOW MUCH CONFIDENCE
THEY HAVE IN THEMSELVES.
NOT EVEN BACK IN MY DAYS WITH
THE RED SUNS DID ANYONE SEEM TO
BLOW US OFF AS MUCH AS THESE
GUYS ARE DOING RIGHT NOW.
- YOU KNOW FUMIHIRO, YOU CAN GET
BENT OUTTA SHAPE IF YOU WANT,
BUT THAT KINDA STUFF
NEVER BOTHERED ME.
- HUH?
- BEFORE I JOINED THIS TEAM,
I DROVE AGAINST A BUNCH OF
DIFFERENT PEOPLE AND THEY ALWAYS
TREATED ME EXACTLY LIKE THIS.
I'M USED TO IT.
I CONCENTRATE BETTER WHEN I
DON'T KNOW MY OPPONENT I LIKE
IT WHEN IT'S A STRANGER
IN THE OTHER CAR.
PUSH ALL THE UNNECESSARY
THOUGHTS OUT OF YOUR HEAD AND
JUST FOCUS ON DRIVING
AS FAST AS YOU CAN
ON THE ROAD IN FRONT OF YOU.
I'M HAVING A LOT OF FUN.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
- YOU SERIOUS?
- I DON'T KNOW ANY OTHER WAY TO
EXPLAIN IT. I JUST CAN'T THINK
OF ANYTHING I LIKE MORE.
THERE'S NOTHING BETTER.
- I SEE. PUT IT LIKE THAT,
AND I GUESS THAT'S THE
WAY YOU'VE ALWAYS RACED.
- GOOD POINT.
- AMAZING. I CAN'T
BELIEVE HE CAN RELAX
AND ENJOY THIS SITUATION
AS MUCH AS HE IS.
FUJIWARA'S ON A LEVEL
TOTALLY DIFFERENT
FROM RYOSUKE OR KEISUKE.
AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX,
TAKUMI FUJIWARA.
AND NOW THAT WE'RE BOTH HERE,
THERE'S NO POINT IN
STIRRING UP ANY TROUBLE.
I THINK THE BEST THING WE CAN
DO, IS TO STAND BEHIND THE
DOWNHILL DRIVER
THAT RYOSUKE'S CHOSEN.
- IS THAT YOU, DAIKI?
- I WANNA RUN A QUICK CHECK ON
MY BRAKES. DO YOU MIND IF I
BORROW A JACK AND A
WRENCH FOR A FEW MINUTES?
- THAT'S COOL.
SO, IS THIS PART THE RITUAL OF
"FINAL CHECK PREPARATION"
BEFORE TONIGHT'S BIG RACE?
- NOW YOU KNOW I'VE NEVER BEEN
INTO THAT KINDA BS.
- ( sighs )
- TO BE HONEST WITH
YOU I CAN'T GET
PUMPED UP FOR THIS ONE, SAKAI.
FOR SOME REASON I
JUST CAN'T GET INTO THIS BATTLE.
- YEAH, I COULD TELL
SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ACTING LIKE
YOURSELF SINCE YESTERDAY.
IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH YOUR
OPPONENT'S CAR, RIGHT?
- DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS SO OBVIOUS.
BUT OF COURSE YOU'D
BE ABLE TO TELL.
OUT OF ALL THE CARS TO
GO UP AGAINST, AN EIGHT-SIX!
TO CHASE AFTER A WIND-UP TOY
LIKE THAT AND LEAVE IT IN THE
DUST-IT'S LIKE BEATING
UP A LITTLE KID.
- ( laughs )
- ONCE I SAW THAT CAR LAST
NIGHT, I'VE FELT BAD EVER SINCE.
I DON'T CARE IF THE DRIVER'S THE
BEST IN THE WORLD, I CAN'T FIND
ANYTHING THAT EXCITES
ME ABOUT THIS RACE.
THIS WHOLE THING WOULD BE A LOT
BETTER IF I WAS RACING THE FD.
- SO YOU'LL EMBARRASS HIM. BIG
DEAL. YOU'VE GOTTA STOP BEING
SO PARTICULAR. EVERYONE
KNOWS THAT IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT CAR YOU'RE RACING AGAINST.
NO CAR IS EVER GONNA BEAT
YOU IN A DOWNHILL RACE.
NOW CHANGE THAT LOCKED-UP WAY
YOU'VE BEEN THINKING AND SHOW
THESE JERKS THE DIFFERENCE
IN YOUR SKILLS.
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO PICKED THE
FIGHT, PAL. REMEMBER THAT.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR US
TO HOLD BACK AT ALL.
EVEN IF YOUR OPPONENT IS A
PATHETIC, LITTLE EIGHT-SIX.
- I'M TAKUMI FUJIWARA.
- I'M DAIKI NINOMIYA.
HE'S SO YOUNG. THIS IS PROJECT
D'S DOWNHILL RACER?
- WE WANNA RUN THE RACE IN
THE LEADER/CHASER FASHION
IF IT'S ALRIGHT BY YOU.
IT'S YOUR TRACK SO YOU GUYS
CAN CHOOSE YOUR POSITION
FOR THE FIRST RUN.
- YOU THINK THAT THROUGH?
WE'RE ALREADY GOT THE ADVANTAGE
BEING THE HOME TEAM HERE.
- YEAH, BUT THIS IS HOW WE'D
PREFER TO DO THINGS
WHEN WE'RE THE AWAY TEAM.
- YOU GUYS ARE PRETTY
CONFIDENT, AREN'T YOU?
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN I'LL BE THE ONE CHASING.
SWITCH UP ON THE SECOND RUN.
- GOOD. THEN WE SHOULD GO
AHEAD AND START THE RACE.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY BEING
THE CHASER? YOU'D JUST FINISH
THE RACE ALL THAT MUCH SOONER IF
YOU TOOK THE LEADER SLOT.
- YOU MAY BE RIGHT. BUT
SOMETHING'S BEEN NAGGING AT ME.
- YOU GET IT, RIGHT?
THIS GUY IS NOT GONNA BE AS EASY
AN OPPONENT AS WE THOUGHT.
- SO, THEY'RE GONNA BE CHASING
FOR THE FIRST RUN? ALRIGHT...
COULDJA HAND THE PHONE
OVER TO TAKUMI?
- FUJIWARA, IT'S RYOSUKE.
- WHAT'S UP?
- TAKUMI, IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT YOU LISTEN
I HAVE TWO BASIC
INSTRUCTIONS FOR YOU.
- Takumi: OKAY. OKAY.
SURE, I UNDERSTAND.
- WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU, MAN.
- I HOPE I CAN DO IT...
THIS GUY'S AN INCREDIBLE DRIVER.
I CAN SENSE IT. IT'S LIKE I
CAN SEE HOW FAST HE IS.
HE'S AMAZING.
- ( car engine revving )
- Fumihiro: YOU BOTH
START OFF SLOW
AND THEN AFTER THE FIRST
CORNER, YOU CAN
KICK IT INTO FULL SPEED
AND GIVE IT ALL SHE'S GOT.
THE EIGHT-SIX IS STARTING
OFF FIRST.
SO YOU JUST HAVE TO
STAY BEHIND IT.
- I GOT IT.
- ( revving engine )
- THAT EIGHT-SIX'S DRIVER SEEMS
LIKE HE'S GOT MORE TO GIVE THAT
I WAS GIVING HIM CREDIT FOR.
THERE'S ONLY ONE REASON I CHOSE
TO BE THE CHASER FOR THE FIRST
RUN, I HAVE TO KNOW.
WHY DOES HE DRIVE AN EIGHT-SIX?
I MEAN, WHAT CAN HE POSSIBLY
DO IN A SCRAP-HEAP LIKE THAT?
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'VE GOT.
- ( revving engine )
- HERE WE GO! LET'S DO THIS!
- ALRIGHT, THEY'RE STARTING UP!
- IT'S ABOUT TIME THIS
DOWNHILL GOT GOING'.
- HEY, CAN YOU HEAR ME? YEAH,
THEY'RE ABOUT TO START!
- IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT WHAT
PROJECT D IS REALLY MADE OF.
- (theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ WHO YOU WANNA BE,
WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA SEE,
WHAT YOU WANNA SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪