- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( car engine revving )
- ( upbeat techno
music playing )
- ( chattering indistinctly )
- THOSE GUYS'RE KILLIN' IT!
- HOLD UP! WHY IS DAIKI'S
EK-NINE DOING THE CHASING?
- MAYBE IT'S CUZ THEY KNEW
THE RACE WOULD BE OVER
BEFORE IT STARTED IF HE
WAS OUT IN FRONT.
- SO YOU THINK THE GUY'S
JUST SHOWING OFF?
- WHOA! TELL YOU ONE THING,
THE GUY DRIVING THAT EIGHT-SIX
KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT. I MEAN,
HE JUST SHOT THROUGH THERE LIKE
THIS WAS SOME KINDA
STRAIGHTAWAY.
- Ryosuke: I EXPECTED THAT
DAIKI WOULD WANNA LEAD.
BUT HE CHOSE TO CHASE INSTEAD.
AN IMPRESSIVE DECISION,
AND A REALLY SMART ONE.
- HEY, BRO?
- YEAH?
- WHEN YOU JUMPED ON THE PHONE
WITH FUJIWARA RIGHT BEFORE THE
RACE STARTED, YOU TOLD HIM
SOMETHING. WHAT WAS THE ADVICE?
- I WOULDN'T GO SO FAR
AS TO SAY I GAVE HIM ADVICE.
I JUST HAD TWO BASIC
INSTRUCTIONS TO GIVE HIM.
- AND THEY WERE?
- NOT TO LOOK INTO HIS REARVIEW
MIRROR. NO MATTER WHAT, DON'T
LOOK INTO IT UNTIL THE
FIRST HEAT IS OVER.
- WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T SEE HOW THAT WOULD
IMPROVE HIS TIMING IN THE RACE.
- DIDN'T SOME IDIOT LAST NIGHT
SPOUT OFF ABOUT RACING OTHER
TEAMS BEING FUN? YEAH, RIGHT,
THEY'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
THIS GUY COULD COMPETE IN A RACE
WITH THE TOUDOU SCHOOL GUYS
RIGHT NOW AND GIVE THEM
A REAL RUN FOR THEIR MONEY.
WHO THE HELL IS HE?
IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S BEEN
ANYONE IN THE TOUDOU SCHOOL'S
HISTORY WHO COULD DRIVE THIS
WELL ON A COURSE AFTER
PRACTICING FOR JUST ONE NIGHT.
AND WE'RE THE BEST THERE IS.
OF COURSE, I HAVE NO IDEA HOW
MUCH HIS ENGINE'S BEEN TUNED.
BUT I KNOW THAT IT REVS JUST AS
HIGH AS MY CARS B16B ENGINE.
THE SUCKER CORNERS TIGHTER
THAN AN L BRACKET.
THAT CAR ISN'T AN EIGHT-SIX!
DOES THIS MEAN THAT EVEN AN
FR CAN RUN LIKE THIS
IF YOU HAVE IT TUNED PROPERLY?
YOU MIGHT HAVE BEEN ON A
WINNING STREAK BEFORE,
USING THAT CAR IN ALL
THOSE "AWAY" RACES.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOUR
LUCK HAS RUN OUT.
YOUR ONE OUR TURF NOW!
THIS IS THE HOME COURSE
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL.
- Sakai: I MEAN EVEN THOUGH
HE'S BEEN TRASHING
THE GUY'S EIGHT-SIX
THIS WHOLE TIME,
HE MUST'VE PUT SOMETHING
TOGETHER IN THAT HEAD OF HIS
RIGHT BEFORE THE RACE, BECAUSE
HIS WHOLE ATTITUDE CHANGED.
THAT HAD TO BE WHY HE
AGREED TO BE THE CHASER.
IF IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
ME IN THAT CAR,
I LIKE TO THINK I WOULD HAVE
MADE THE SAME CALL.
I'D WANNA SEE HOW THESE GUYS WHO
ARE SUPPOSEDLY THE FASTEST IN
GOON-MUH DRIVE.
BEST WAY TO DO THAT IS TO
FOLLOW RIGHT BEHIND'EM.
AND IF THE DUDE COULDN'T DO ANY
BETTER THAN A HALF-ASSED
PERFORMANCE, I'D JUST
BLOW RIGHT PAST HIM
AND PUT A PERIOD ON THE
END OF THE RACE.
YOU HAVE A POINT THERE, SAKAI.
AND ISN'T DAIKI
SUPPOSED TO BE THE BEST DRIVER
AMONG THE CURRENT STUDENTS?
WHAT'S HE GOOD AT ANYWAY?
- WELL, MAKE OF IT WHAT YOU WILL
BUT DAIKI'S GOOD AT BRAKING.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN, IT MAY NOT
SOUND THAT IMPRESSIVE BUT...
- IT'S ACTUALLY AN
EXCELLENT SKILL TO HAVE.
THERE'S NO BETTER WEAPON AT
YOUR DISPOSAL ON THE DOWNHILL.
AS A TOUDOU SCHOOL STUDENT
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN TAUGHT
THAT ON DAY ONE.
- Ryosuke: IF HE'S GONNA
BE THE ONE CHASING,
I WANT YOU TO LISTEN
TO ME VERY CAREFULLY TAKUMI.
I DON'T WANT YOU LOOKING
IN THAT REARVIEW
UNTIL THE FIRST RUN IS FINISHED.
I WANT YOUR FOCUS ON
MASTERING THE COURSE.
IF YOU DRIVE LIKE YOU
NORMALLY DO,
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE ANY TROUBLE
NOT BEING PASSED.
YOU UNDERSTAND? THIS IS VERY
IMPORTANT. DO NOT LOOK BACK.
- I THINK I FIGURED OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH THIS EIGHT-SIX.
IT RUNS A WHOLE LOT
BETTER THAN I EXPECTED.
BUT I STILL DON'T THINK
IT'S ENOUGH TO WORRY ABOUT.
MY SCHOOL'S REPUTATION
IS ON THE LINE.
I NEED TO END THIS BEFORE
THE SECOND RUN.
BUT THAT MEANS PASSING
HIM SOMEWHERE.
I'LL HAVE TO CREATE THE
OPPORTUNITY BY PUSHING HIM.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HOW LONG
HE CAN HOLD OUT WITH ME!
♪ SPEED CAR, SPEED CAR ♪
- THEY'RE SO CLOSE!
HOW'RE THEY DOING THIS?
- ONE LITTLE HITCH AND BOTH
THOSE DUDES ARE GONNA CRASH!
- EVERYONE KNOWS THAT IN THIS
CLASS OF CARS THE FF'S ARE JUST
PLAIN FASTER THAN THE FR'S.
BUT ON TOP UH THAT,
MY CAR IS THE ULTIMATE,
IT'S THE TYPE R.
I CAN'T BE COLLECTING DUST
BEHIND THIS EIGHT-SIX
FOR VERY LONG.
I'M ENDING THIS THING
ON THE FIRST RUN!
- TS guy: AS A DRIVER BRAKES
GOING INTO A CORNER,
THE MOMENT THAT HE LETS HIS FOOT
UP AND STOPS BRAKING IS WAY MORE
IMPORTANT THAN WHEN
HE PUSHES DOWN TO START.
THE MOMENTS OF
DECELERATION AND ACCELERATION
NEED TO BE PRECISE, CALCULATED.
TOO SOON OR TOO LATE AND THEY
CAN BOTH LEAD TO A LOSS OF TIME.
A DRIVER WITH A KILLER TECHNIQUE
CAN ALWAYS FIND HIS WAY OUT OF A
MISTAKE THAT HE MAKES. BUT ON
ANY GIVEN CORNER, THERE'S ONLY
ONE PERFECT PLACE TO LET OFF OF
THAT BRAKE. EVEN THE BEST
DRIVER'S OUT THERE CAN'T RECOVER
FROM SCREWING THAT UP.
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE. CHIEF
ALWAYS SAID BRAKING IS THE MOST
DIFFICULT TECHNIQUE TO MASTER
WHEN IT COMES TO DRIVING A CAR.
- NO OTHER TECHNIQUE CAN
EVEN COME CLOSE TO IT.
- HE'S A SMART MAN.
- DAIKI'S EXPERTISE IS IN
DETERMINING JUST WHERE
THAT POINT IS IN A CORNER.
NO MATTER HOW LONG HE'S HAD HIS
FOOT ON THE BRAKE, HE YANKS IT
OFF RIGHT ON THE
MONEY EVERY SINGLE TIME.
HE'S NEVER EARLY AND NEVER LATE.
HE'S A NATURAL I CAN'T
EXPLAIN IT ANY OTHER WAY.
IT'S ALL INSTINCT.
- Toudou: LISTEN UP, DAIKI.
THESE DAYS ANTILOCK BRAKING
SYSTEMS ARE A STANDARD IN THE
RACING WORLD. LET'S YA KNOW HOW
WELL THAT SYSTEM'S GOTTA WORK
FOR EVERYONE TO USE IT.
BUT HERE AT THE TOUDOU SCHOOL,
WE'VE MADE IT A POINT TO
DITCH IT COMPLETELY. NO ABS.
THE FIRST THING YOU GOTTA
LEARN IS HOW TO BREAK
WITHOUT RELYING ON
ALL THAT CRAP.
YOU CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW
TO USE THE ABS
UNTIL YOU'VE MASTERED THE
BRAKING SYSTEM WITHOUT IT.
IT'S YOUR FIRST LESSON. AND I
EXPECT YOU TO LIVE AND BREATHE
IT UNTIL YOU'RE BRAKING
IN YOUR SLEEP.
IT'S ONE OF THE CHIEF
PRINCIPALS OF MY SCHOOL.
♪ SPEED CAR! SPEED CAR!
AE EIGHTY-SIX IS COMING ♪
♪ SPEED CAR! SPEED CAR! ♪
♪ AND HE'S GONNA BE THE ONE.
SPEED CAR! ♪
- THERE MAY NOT BE A
CENTER LINE ON THIS ROAD
BUT THE SUCKER IS PLENTY WIDE.
I GOT MY PICK UP PLACES WHERE I
CAN PASS THIS GUY. BUT, EVERY
TIME I PULL CLOSE USING
MY BRAKING,
I MISS MY CHANCE TO
PASS BY A HAIR.
I HAD NO CLUE THAT AN FR
COULD CORNER THIS QUICKLY.
♪ SPEED CAR! SPEED CAR! ♪
♪ IT'S THE TEAM OF PROJECT D,
THEY'RE WINNING ♪
- THEY MUST BE CRAZY DRIVING
THAT CLOSE TOGETHER. SERIOUSLY.
- C'MON THEY'RE THAT CLOSE
BECAUSE NINOMIYA'S
EK-NINE IS WAY FASTER
AND HE'S JUST TRYING TO
GET HIM OUTTA THE WAY.
AN EIGHT-SIX IS TOO SLOW
TO BE OUT HERE RACING .
- YOU'RE WRONG. I DON'T THINK
IT'S THAT EASY OF AN ANSWER.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD
STICK THAT CLOSE TO SOMEONE
IF THEY WERE DRIVING SLOW.
YOU DON'T STICK SO TIGHTLY TO
SOMEONE'S BUMPER UNLESS YOU HAVE
A LOT OF TRUST IN THE
GUY IN FRONT OF YOU.
IF YOU ASK ME, THE DRIVER
OF THAT EIGHT-SIX
HAS GOT TO BE INCREDIBLY FAST.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- YEAH. I'VE NEVER SEEN DAIKI
STICK SO CLOSE TO A BUMPER
BEFORE, NOT EVEN DURING A RACE
BETWEEN TOUDOU SCHOOL STUDENTS.
GUESS THE GUY WHO
ALWAYS PLAYS IT COOL
IS GETTING A LITTLE HOT
UNDER THE COLLAR.
- HIS FOCUS ON THE
ROAD IS UNBELIEVABLE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW
MUCH I PRESS THIS GUY,
I CAN'T GET ANY KIND OF
REACTION OUT OF HIM.
EVEN THE STUDENTS AT SCHOOL
WOULD SHOW SOME KIND OF REACTION
IF I WENT THIS FAR
TO PRESSURE THEM.
- I DON'T EVEN NEED TO LOOK
INTO MY REARVIEW
TO KNOW HE'S BEHIND ME.
AND RIGHT ON MY BUMPER.
I CAN FEEL THE PRESSURE AGAINST
MY BACK. IT'S ALMOST PAINFUL.
BUT ONCE I MADE UP MY MIND TO
NOT LOOK BACK THERE, IT MADE IT
A WHOLE LOT EASIER TO
CONCENTRATE ON THIS COURSE.
RYOSUKE ONLY GAVE ME TWO
SIMPLE INSTRUCTIONS.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS FOLLOW 'EM.
- OKAY, BRO. SO, WHAT'S THE
OTHER ONE YOU TOLD HIM?
- HMM?
- THE OTHER THING YOU TOLD
TAKUMI BEFORE HE WENT OUT THERE.
- IT'S REAL SIMPLE.
REV-LIMITING.
IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW, THAT
EIGHT-SIX OF HIS REVS UP TO
ELEVEN THOUSAND RPM'S. BUT I
TOLD HIM TO STAY OFF THE TOP TWO
THOUSAND RPM'S AND
THAT HE SHOULD RESORT
TO JUST SHIFTING UP
AT NINE THOUSAND MARK.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS?
WHY WOULD YOU HAVE HIM DO
SOMETHING STUPID LIKE THAT?
- BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT HIM
SHOWING ALL OF HIS CAPABILITIES
TO HIS OPPONENT RIGHT
OUT OF THE GATE.
AFTER ALL, WE BOTH KNOW
FUJIWARA ISN'T QUITE READY
TO PLAY MIND GAMES JUST YET.
IN AN EFFORT NOT TO CLOUD HIS
MIND WITH TOO MUCH CONFUSION AND
OVER THINKING, THIS SEEMED
LIKE THE BEST WAY
I COULD GET THE RESULTS
THAT I WANTED.
I KNOW IT'S SOME RISKY BUSINESS
TO HOLD BACK YOUR ABILITIES
AGAINST AN OPPONENT OF THE
CALIBER HE'S GOT TONIGHT.
BUT IF HE MANAGES TO HOLD HIS
OWN AND SURVIVE THE FIRST RUN,
THEN I SHOULD BE ABLE TO CREATE
A WINNING SIMULATION.
I'M AWARE IT'S AN ENORMOUS
GAMBLE I'M PLACING.
- THAT'S RISKY.
HE'S STAYING AHEAD OF THE TOUDOU
SCHOOL'S DOWNHILLER.
AND HE'S GOT HIS TOP TWO
THOUSAND RPM'S SEALED OFF?
WHEN DID HE GET THE SKILLS TO
ATTEMPT SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
HE'S ALWAYS HAD IT.
THIS GUY CAN ADAPT TO ANY
SITUATION YOU THROW AT HIM.
WHAT HE'S TRYING TO DO REQUIRES
A DEGREE OF CONCENTRATION
GREATER THAN HE'S
EVER HAD TO USE.
- MAKES SENSE. THAT'S
WHY YOU TOLD HIM
TO KEEP HIS EYES OFF HIS
REARVIEW MIRROR.
THAT WAY THERE'S NO CHANCE HE'D
BE AFFECTED BY THE PRESSURE OF
HIS OPPONENT BEARING DOWN ON HIM
AND BREAKING HIS FOCUS.
- IT'S INCREDIBLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I NEVER EXPECTED IT TO
BE THIS CRAZY TONIGHT.
I MADE A BIG MISTAKE BY
CHASING ON THE FIRST RUN.
EVERY MOVE I MAKE LOOKS LIKE
I'M STRUGGLING BACK HERE.
- ( engine revving )
- ALRIGHT, HERE COMES
THE SECOND RUN?
- I SAW ENOUGH OF WHAT THE
EIGHT-SIX AND IT'S DRIVER CAN DO
IN THE FIRST RUN.
I GOT THIS LOCKED DOWN.
THEY DON'T HAVE WHAT
IT TAKES TO BEAT ME.
THEY JUST DON'T HAVE THE SPEED.
THIS'LL BE OVER IN SECONDS.
HE'S FAST!
- NOT GOOD.
THIS GUY'S GOT SPEED.
NO ROOM FOR MISTAKES. I'M RIDING
THE RAZOR'S EDGE ON THIS RUN.
HE'S GOING AT A PACE
THAT'S A LOT FASTER
THAN THE FIRST TIME AROUND.
AM I REALLY GONNA BE ABLE TO
KEEP UP WITH THIS GUY?
- WHEN FUJIWARA'S THE
ONE WHO'S CHASING,
HE HOLDS A STAGGERING DEGREE
OF CONCENTRATION.
HIS ABILITY TO ADAPT
TO A PACE HE'S
NEVER EXPERIENCED BEFORE IS
GREATER THAN SKILL.
IT'S MORE LIKE INSTINCT.
IF HE'S BEING PULLED ALONG BY A
LOCAL DRIVER WHO'S FASTER THAN
HE IS, HE'LL METHODICALLY
MAKE THE OPPONENT'S SPEED
INTO HIS OWN.
IF THIS WHOLE THING WORKS OUT
LIKE MY SIMULATION SAYS IT WILL,
THEN HE SHOULD HAVE
NO PROBLEM BEATING THEM.
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU, TAKUMI.
IT'S ALL ON YOU NOW.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I SHOULD HAVE FIGURED OUT HIS
TOP SPEED ON THAT FIRST RUN.
I KNOW I'M MOVING AT A FASTER
PACE THAN THAT NOW. HE SHOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO KEEP UP
WITH ME AT ALL.
WHAT ARE YOU STILL
DOING BACK THERE?
- THIS IS STARTING TO SCARE ME.
I'VE NEVER KNOWN A DOWNHILL TO
BE THIS FRIGHTENING BEFORE.
IF I LET OFF OF THE ACCELERATOR,
I CAN RELEASE THIS
FEAR. I KNOW IT.
BUT THERE'S THIS OTHER PART
OF ME THAT'S SAYING
"WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T LET GO."
- NO WAY.
ALL RIGHT. SO ACCORDING TO THE
GUYS AT THE FIRST HAIRPIN TURN,
THERE'S NO DISTANCE
BETWEEN THE TWO.
WHAT? I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
THINK WE GOT A PROBLEM HERE.
- I STILL CAN'T SHAKE HIM! HE'S
KEEPING STEADY WITH A PACE
THAT'S TWICE AS FAST
AS OUR FIRST RUN!
- IF FUJIWARA CAN KEEP UP, AN
INTERESTING FACTOR WILL EMERGE.
IT'LL HAPPEN IN THE SECOND
HALF OF THE COURSE
AND WILL BE AN
ENORMOUS ADVANTAGE.
ANY IDEA WHAT THAT
MIGHT BE KENTA?
- I MEAN, NO, UH, TO BE HONEST,
THE WHOLE THING'S
KINDA CONFUSING.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- I GET THE BASIC GIST
OF WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
IT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN AN
FF AND AN FR. IN AN FR,
IT'S THE JOB OF THE REAR TIRES
TO DO ALL THE ACCELERATION.
THEY PUSH THE CAR.
AN FF OVERUSES THE FRONT TIRES.
FOR BOTH ACCELERATION
AND CORNERING.
A DOWNHILL RACE BY ITS NATURE IS
ALREADY GONNA PUT STRESS
ON THE FRONT TIRES OF A CAR.
SO THAT EK-NINE, BEING
A FRONT WHEEL DRIVE,
IS GONNA HAVE IT'S FRONT TIRES
GIVE OUT FIRST.
- DAMN!
THIS IS BAD. I THOUGHT I'D
BEAT HIM IN THE FIRST RUN
SO I PUSHED MY CAR WAY TOO HARD.
THAT WAS THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
I COULD HAVE MADE!
I PUT TOO MUCH
STRESS ON MY TIRES!
- Ryosuke: THIS WHOLE IDEA
OF REV-LIMITING
WAS PART OF A
DISTURBANCE TACTIC.
A DRIVER WITH ENOUGH SKILLS WILL
BE ABLE TO LEARN EVERYTHING
ABOUT HIS OPPONENT'S ABILITIES
SIMPLY BY FOLLOWING BEHIND HIM
FOR ENOUGH TIME.
THEN HE'LL DETERMINE NOT ONLY
WHERE TO MAKE HIS PASS,
BUT HOW...
- SO, THE GUY IN FRONT
WEARS DOWN HIS TIRES
AND HIS BRAKES EVEN MORE.
- EXACTLY.
- THAT'S REALLY AMAZING MAN. I
GUESS I HAD NO IDEA THOSE TWO
PIECES OF ADVICE HAD SUCH DEEP
MEANINGS BEHIND THEM.
- THE IMPORTANT STUFF
HAPPENS FROM HERE ON OUT.
THE TIRES ON THE EIGHT-SIX
WON'T LAST FOR MUCH
LONGER EITHER. EVERYTHING NOW
IS LEFT UP TO WHETHER
OR NOT TAKUMI
CAN CAPITALIZE ON THAT ADVANTAGE
HE'S BEEN GIVEN.
♪ REVOLUTION
WAKE UP THE SLEEPY SAMURAI ♪
♪ FIGHTIN' IN YOUR SPIRIT
REVOLUTION ♪
♪ YOU GOT THE FIRE IN YOU,
IN YOUR HEART ♪
- I'M NOT IMAGINING
THIS AFTER ALL.
HIS CORNERING IS GETTING SLOWER.
IS IT HIS TIRES? I WONDER IF
THEY'RE STARTING TO GIVE OUT
UNDER THE STRESS. MINE STILL
SEEM TO HAVE PLENTY OF GRIP,
BUT WHO KNOWS HOW
LONG THAT'LL LAST.
IT'S TIME TO PASS THIS PATHETIC
EK, AND PUT THIS BATTLE TO BED.
- IF YOU WERE UP THERE BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF THE EIGHT-SIX,
WHERE WOULD YOU MAKE
THE MOVE TO PASS?
- THERE ARE PLACES ON ANY COURSE
WHERE THE MORE YOU PUSH YOUR
CAR, THE MORE DIFFICULT
IT IS TO FIND
THE RIGHT PLACE TO SHIFT GEARS.
I'M SURE YOU'VE
EXPERIENCED THIS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THOSE POINTS
LIKE WHERE YOU'RE HEADING INTO A
CORNER AND YOU
HESITATE FOR A MOMENT
WHILE YOU DECIDED WHETHER
OR NOT TO UPSHIFT.
- YEAH, SURE. I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, WHEN THE
TACHOMETER IS IN THE RED ZONE
BUT THERE STILL ISN'T ENOUGH
ROOM LEFT IN FRONT OF
YOU TO SHIFT GEARS
AND ACCELERATE INTO THE TURN.
WHEN YOU'RE IN A MOMENT
LIKE THAT, YOU CAN'T DO
ANYTHING ELSE BUT WAIT IT OUT.
IT'S SO ANNOYING.
TALK ABOUT BEING TIED DOWN.
YOU CAN'T GO FASTER,
YOU CAN'T SLOW DOWN.
YOU'RE JUST SCREWED.
- THAT'S IT. THAT'S
WHAT YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT.
I THINK I GET IT, BRO.
IT'S ALL IN THE ENGINE
OF THE EIGHT-SIX.
IT REV'S HIGHER THAN THE ENGINE
OF THE EK-NINE.
THAT'S THE KEY TO
THIS WHOLE THING.
THE WHOLE POINT WAS TO SEAL OFF
HIS TOP TWO THOUSAND RPM'S.
YOU DIDN'T WANT THE GUY FROM
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL
TO HAVE ANY IDEA THEY
WERE EVEN THERE.
THAT WAS IT.
- WHAT?
- HE BEAT ME. IT'S OVER.
BUT BRAKING IS MY THING, IT'S
WHAT I DO BEST.
AND HE STILL PASSED ME!
- HEY, MAN
- I LOST. I'M SORRY GUYS.
- ANY IDEA HOW THE
HELL THAT HAPPENED?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D ACTUALLY
LOSE ON YOUR HOME COURSE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- GOTTA ADMIT, I'M
IMPRESSED, FUJIWARA.
I THINK YOU DID ONE HELLUVA
JOB OUT THERE TONIGHT.
- I'M GLAD I DID IT. I MAY HAVE
GOTTEN CAUGHT UP IN THE INSANITY
OF THE MOMENT AND SWEAT BULLETS
WHEN I WAS STRAPPED IN. IT'S NOT
THAT OFTEN I SEE RYOSUKE
LOOKING LIKE THAT. HE'S HAPPY.
I MUST HAVE LIVED UP TO
HIS EXPECTATION THIS TIME.
IT FEELS GOOD.
- DO YOUR BEST OUT THERE,
KEISUKE. I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
- I'M READY. AND I'M GONNA
PUSH IT TO THE LIMIT
ON THE VERY FIRST RUN.
- Fumihiro: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE'RE GONNA START
THE UPHILL NOW!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ WHO YOU WANNA BE
WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA SEE,
WHAT YOU WANNA SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪