- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HEY, TAKUMI! YOU OFF TODAY?
- OH, YEAH.
- TAKUMI! IT'S
FINALLY HAPPENING!
- WHAT'S GOT YOU SO WORKED UP?
- OH, C'MON YOU KNOW!
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE LEVIN!
BABY'S GETTING FITTED
WITH A TURBO!
- NO KIDDING?
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU,
SHE'S IN THE SHOP AS WE SPEAK.
THIS IS TOTALLY GONNA
KICK ALL KINDS OF ASS!
- WAIT, LET ME GET
THIS STRAIGHT.
THAT TURTLE-BUCKET
OF YOURS MIGHT GET
FROM POINT A TO B
WITHOUT BREAKING DOWN?
- IS THAT FEAR I DETECT?
OH, JUST YOU WAIT AND SEE.
WITH THE TURBO INSTALLED
THAT PUPPY'LL HIT 180 HORSEPOWER
LIKE IT WAS NOTHING.
THE DAYS OF ME
FALLING BEHIND YOU
AND YOUR FLASHY
LITTLE S-THIRTEEN
ON THE HILL CLIMB ARE OVER,
MY FRIEND!
( laughs )
- 180, HUH?
TURBOS ARE GREAT
AND ALL, SURE, BUT...
- Iketani: AH, LET HIM DREAM...
SO MR. ALL-STAR,
KENJI TELLS ME YOU'VE GOT
BEATING THE TOUDOU SCHOOL
UNDER YOUR BELT NOW.
- YEAH, I GUESS I DO.
- I HEAR KEISUKE SLAUGHTERED
EVERYONE ON THE HILL CLIMB,
BUT IT WAS YOUR PERFECTLY
TIMED ATTACKS
THAT REALLY SEALED THE DEAL.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE THOSE POOR
GUYS DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
WAY TO GO, PROJECT D.
- WITH MY NEW 8-5 TURBO,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THEY'RE
BEGGING ME TO JOIN!
- (laughs ) NOW THAT
I'D LIKE TO SEE.
- ( tires screeching )
- TOMOYUKI.
- WORD ON THE STREET IS
YOU TWO GOT DUSTED.
HOW DID IT GO DOWN?
I WANT DETAILS.
- IN A WAY, THEY NEEDED TO LOSE.
NOTHING KEEPS A TEAM FOCUSED
LIKE A GOOD DOSE OF HUMILITY.
OF COURSE THAT'S ASSUMING
THEY GET THE LESSON.
HOWEVER GOOD YOU ARE,
THERE'S ALWAYS GONNA BE
ANOTHER WALL AROUND THE CORNER,
JUST WAITIN' TO BE HIT.
DAIKI AND SAKAI
FOUND THAT OUT THE HARD WAY
AFTER RACING PROJECT D
THE OTHER NIGHT.
THE TRICK IS NOT TO GET
TOO COMFORTABLE.
WHEN YOU LOSE, YOU'VE GOTTA
SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE
AND LEARN FROM IT.
YOU'LL FIND YOUR LIMIT.
WE ALL DO.
I GOTTA TELL YOU THOUGH, KID,
I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN HITTIN'
YOUR WALL LATELY,
BUT I'M JUST NOT CONVINCED
THAT IT'S SOMETHING
YOU WON'T BE ABLE GET OVER.
- WAIT A SEC. YOU KNOW ABOUT ALL
THE CRAP I'VE BEEN DEALING WITH?
- I CAN SEE IT IN THE WAY
YOU'RE DRIVING.
HELL IF I COULDN'T I'D HARDLY
BE CHIEF OF THE TOUDOU SCHOOL.
IT'S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE.
- WHAT CAN I SAY?
THINGS HAVE BEEN ROUGH.
IT FEELS LIKE PROFESSIONAL
RACING IS ALL ABOUT FUNDING
AND SPONSORSHIP NOW.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH TO STAY FOCUSED
AND KEEP YOUR TEAM'S MORALE UP
WITHOUT WORRYING ABOUT FINDING
A BACKER IN THIS DAMN RECESSION.
I LET IT GET TO ME WHEN MY MIND
SHOULD BE ON THE COURSE.
I LOSE GROUND
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS,
AND THEN I END UP LEAVING
MYSELF OPEN TO MAKE MISTAKES
EVEN A ROOKIE WOULDN'T MAKE.
I'M LOSING MY PASSION FOR
THE RACE BECAUSE OF IT,
THE WHOLE THING'S BECOMING
A VICIOUS CYCLE.
MAYBE I HAVE FINALLY HIT A WALL
THAT I WON'T BE
ABLE TO OVERCOME.
- NO OFFENSE, BUT
IF THAT WERE TRUE,
I DOUBT YOU'D TAKE IT LYING
DOWN LIKE THIS.
- HUH?
- PROBLEM IS YOU CAN'T SEE THE
FOREST FOR THE TREES RIGHT NOW,
KID, YOU NEED A DISTRACTION.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- YOU KNOW, A STREET RACE
MIGHT DO YOU GOOD.
WHY NOT GIVE IT A SHOT?
- THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE
SERIOUS ABOUT THAT.
I MEAN, WEREN'T YOU
THE ONE WHO TOLD THAT ME
ONCE I TURNED PRO I SHOULDN'T
RISK HURTING MY REPUTATION
BY TAKING PART IN A STREET RACE?
- SOMETIMES THE RISK
IS WORTH IT.
TAKE ON AN AMATEUR AND SEE
WHAT IT DOES FOR YOUR FOCUS.
IF YOU GET CAUGHT,
YOU CAN ALWAYS TELL THE
SPONSORS HE TRICKED YOU.
HEY, WE ALL GOTTA CUT LOOSE
EVERY NOW AND THEN, RIGHT?
- WELL?
- IT'S ACTUALLY BALANCED
PRETTY WELL.
I WASN'T HARD ON THE ENGINE,
BUT COMPARED TO WHEN WE FIRST
GOT IT INSTALLED
THE DOWNHILLS ARE A BREEZE.
IT'S NOT THE BEST CAR
IN THE WORLD
BUT IT CAN STILL IMPRESS YOU
WHEN IT'S TUNED RIGHT.
AND I'M SURE IT'S MADE RACING
A HELL OF A LOT EASIER FOR YOU.
WELL MAYBE, BUT THE PEOPLE I'M
UP AGAINST KEEP GETTING BETTER.
SOONER OR LATER THIS WINNING
STREAK IS GONNA BREAK.
I CAN'T KEEP IT UP.
- NATURALLY, LOSING'S NOT THE
END OF THE WORLD, YOU KNOW.
MIGHT EVEN TEACH YOU
A THING OR TWO.
- TEACH ME? COME ON, DAD.
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
I'VE TEAMMATES TO THINK ABOUT.
I CAN'T JUST LOSE
FOR THE SAKE OF LOSING.
- PUSHING YOURSELF TO THE
LIMIT MEANS BEING READY
AND WILLING TO ACCEPT
WHAT THAT LIMIT IS.
NO MATTER HOW WELL-TUNED,
EVEN THE BEST CAR IS BOUND BY
THE SAME LAWS OF PHYSICS
AS EVERY OTHER
CAR ON THE ROAD.
- OF COURSE IT IS, BUT WHAT...
- JUST TRY TO MAINTAIN
SOME PERSPECTIVE.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S KINDA FUNNY, FOR
A CAR THAT'S ONLY HALF YOURS,
YOU SURE GET A LOT MORE USE
OUT OF IT THAN ME.
ALL I EVER SEEM TO DO LATELY
IS WORK ON THE DAMN THING.
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO CONSIDER BUYING A NEW ONE.
- YOU'RE JOKING.
- I'M PRETTY SURE IF I PLAYED
MY CARDS RIGHT,
MASASHI WOULD GET ME
A GOOD DEAL ON SOMETHING FUN.
- JUST WHAT KIND OF "FUN"
DO YOU HAVE IN MIND, EXACTLY?
- THAT'S FOR ME TO KNOW.
- Keisuke: HEADS UP, BRO.
I'M COMING IN.
- Ryosuke: ALRIGHT.
- GOOD MORNING.
SO IS IT TRUE WHAT I HEAR
ABOUT THE TOUDOU GUYS
WANTING ANOTHER RACE?
- ONE OF THEIR GRADUATES.
- SERIOUSLY?
- YEAH.
- WE'RE ON, RIGHT?
- ( phone ringing )
- Kyoichi: RYOSUKE...
- Ryosuke: SPEAKING.
- THIS IS KYOICHI.
- AH. TO WHAT DO I OWE
THE PLEASURE?
- I KNOW ONE OF THEIR "ALUMNI"
HAS CHALLENGED PROJECT D
TO A REMATCH ON BEHALF OF
THE TOEDOE SCHOOL.
TAKE MY ADVICE
AND DON'T ACCEPT IT.
I KNOW THAT'S ASKING
THE IMPOSSIBLE,
BUT JUST HEAR ME
OUT FOR A SECOND.
THIS GUY, THE ONE WHO'S
ASKING FOR THE REMATCH...
HE'S A PROFESSIONAL.
NAME'S TOMOYUKI TACHI,
AND HE'S MORE THAN A CUT ABOVE
WHAT YOU'D EXPECT
FROM TOUDOU, BELIEVE ME.
BOTTOM LINE, LOOKS TO ME
LIKE YOU GUYS ARE BEING SET UP.
IF IT'S TOO LATE TO
BACK OUT OF THE RACE,
I RECOMMEND YOU TAKE
HIM ON PERSONALLY.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
IF PROJECT D HAS ANY
SHOT AT WINNING,
IT'S GONNA HAVE TO BE YOU
BEHIND THE WHEEL
WHEN THAT COUNTDOWN STARTS.
YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT.
- ( engine revving )
- WHOA, THE TOUDOU SCHOOL'S
LATEST DEMONSTRATION CAR
ALREADY FLIES LIKE
A BAT OUT OF HELL,
BUT WITH TOMOYUKI DRIVING
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
- NO KIDDING, RIGHT?
I'M GETTING' GOOSEBUMPS
JUST STANDING HERE.
CAN YOU IMAGINE RIDING
SHOTGUN IN THAT THING
WHILE HE RACES PROJECT D?
HE AND THAT CAR
WERE MADE FOR EACH OTHER.
IT'S LIKE WE COULD RACE
OUR WHOLE LIVES
AND NEVER GET ANYWHERE NEAR
THE ZONE HE'S IN RIGHT NOW.
- IT'LL BE EPIC.
EVEN IF I WASN'T IN THIS
TO SEE PROJECT D
TAKEN DOWN A FEW NOTCHES,
I'D CONSIDER MYSELF LUCKY
TO SEE HOW THIS RACE SHAPES UP.
I MEAN, JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
WHEN ARE ANY OF US
EVER GONNA SEE
A BAD-ASS LIKE TOMOYUKI TACHI
TAKE PART IN A FULL-ON
STREET RACE AGAIN?
- SO HOW'S SHE RUN?
- IT'S OKAY I GUESS.
THERE AREN'T ANY PROBLEMS THAT
ARE REALLY WORTH MENTIONING.
FROM HERE ON OUT, IT'S JUST
A QUESTION OF DETAILS.
ALL WE NEED TO DO NOW IS TUNE
THE CAR TO MY PREFERENCES.
HEY, JUST GIVE ME THE WORD
AND SHE'LL FIT YOU LIKE A GLOVE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU NEED.
- OH, I DUNNO.
LOOK, I DON'T GET WHY WE EVEN
NEED TO BOTHER WITH FINE-TUNING
WHEN MY OPPONENT'S
JUST AN AMATEUR.
I MEAN WE'RE ONLY TALKIN'
ABOUT A STREET RACE HERE.
- A STREET RACE IS STILL A RACE.
DON'T GO THINKING OF THIS AS
SOME QUAINT LITTLE EXERCISE.
IF YOU'RE GONNA DO THIS,
DO IT RIGHT.
LEAVE THE PROFESSIONAL
ARENA BEHIND FOR NOW
AND FOCUS ON WHAT'S
IN FRONT OF YOU.
WHEN YOU'RE UP AGAINST
THESE GUYS,
I WANT YOU TO DRIVE LIKE
THE RACE IS ALL THAT MATTERS.
- ALRIGHT, CHIEF,
SINCE YOU PUT IT THAT WAY
I DO HAVE ONE REQUEST.
IF YOU REALLY WANT THE
TOUDOU DEMONSTRATION CAR
TO FIT ME LIKE A GLOVE,
THEN YOU CAN START BY TWEAKING
THE SUSPENSION.
LET'S MAKE IT SO THE
REAR SWINGS OUT MORE
WHEN I'M TAKING A CORNER.
NOT A WHOLE HELLUVA LOT.
JUST ENOUGH TO IMPROVE
MY TIMING A LITTLE BIT.
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
I'LL GIVE YOU WHAT YOU NEED.
- ( gasps )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
SHE LOOKS LIKE A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT CAR NOW.
ALL THAT FROM JUST
REPLACING THE HOOD.
RYOSUKE TOLD US
TO MAKE IT LIGHT.
SO, LITTLE BY LITTLE, THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, THIS BABY'LL
FLOAT LIKE A HOT-AIR BALLOON.
- Ryosuke: OKAY EVERYONE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
THIS IS FOOTAGE OF THE COURSE
WE'LL BE RUNNING,
RECORDED EARLIER TODAY.
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
ONCE YOU'VE WATCHED IT,
BUT THE MIX OF UPHILL AND
DOWNHILL SECTIONS ON THIS THING
PRESENTS AN INTERESTING
CHALLENGE, TO SAY THE LEAST.
- THIS SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
SO HAVE YOU DECIDED YET WHICH
ONE OF US ACTUALLY GETS TO RACE?
- NOT JUST YET.
YOU'LL BOTH RUN THE COURSE.
AND I'LL MAKE UP MY MIND THEN.
WE'RE ALL HEADING OUT THERE
NEXT, SO GET READY.
WHAT THE HELL
IS HE TALKING ABOUT?
I'M THE OBVIOUS CHOICE.
WHAT, WE GOTTA
"AUDITION" NOW?
- THIS RACE IS AN IMPORTANT ONE.
FOR A VARIETY OF REASONS,
NOT LEAST OF WHICH,
WE'RE RACING TOUDOU AGAIN.
- ( both gasp )
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND ON TOP OF THAT, THEY'VE
BROUGHT IN A PROFESSIONAL.
- WHOA. A PROFESSIONAL?
NO WAY.
- BUT RYOSUKE, WITH
ALL DUE RESPECT, WE CAN'T.
WE'RE IN WAY OVER
OUR HEADS HERE.
WE'RE WALKING RIGHT INTO A TRAP.
- THIS IS CRAZY!
WHAT THE HELL ARE WE GONNA DO?
- WE'RE GONNA TREAT
THIS RACE LIKE ANY OTHER.
NOTHING'S WRITTEN IN STONE.
WE STILL HAVE A CHANCE.
BESIDES, THIS IS PROJECT D.
WE DON'T BACK DOWN,
NO MATTER WHO OUR OPPONENT IS.
THAT'S OUR MOTTO.
- DAMN RIGHT.
LET ME TAKE THIS GUY ON.
IF THIS COURSE IS THE CRAZY MIX
OF UPS AND DOWNS YOU SAY IT IS,
THE FD'S TORQUE HAS
THE ADVANTAGE, NO QUESTION.
I SHOULD BE THE ONE
WHO REPRESENTS US.
- Kenta: HE'S RIGHT!
- YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M GETTING
SICK OF HAVING TO REPEAT MYSELF.
I'LL DECIDE WHO RACES
ONCE I'VE SEEN YOU AND TAKUMI
DO YOUR PRACTICE RUNS.
- Daiki: TOMOYUKI.
- OH, IT'S YOU.
- I HEAR THE GUYS IN PROJECT D
ARE PLANNING ON
RUNNING THE COURSE
A FEW TIMES TONIGHT TO PREPARE,
SO IF YOU WANTED,
WE CAN GO AND CHECK OUT
HOW THEY HANDLE IT.
THEY'LL PROBABLY
DRIVE THE COURSE 'TIL DAWN
AND TUNE THEIR
CARS ACCORDINGLY. SO...
- THEY'RE JUST KIDS
WITH TOYS, DAIKI.
KIDS PRETENDING TO BE
PROFESSIONAL DRIVERS
BY DOING THE SAME STUFF WE DO
THE NIGHT BEFORE A BIG RACE.
MAN, THIS IS INSANE.
I'M UP AGAINST A BUNCH OF PUNKS
WHO WOULDN'T KNOW A REAL DRIVER
IF HE HIT THEM.
WHAT WAS THE
CHIEF THINKING?
- I GUESS HE'S SETTING ME
UP FOR A SURE THING
TO BOOST MY CONFIDENCE
OR SOMETHING,
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT IF I
KNOW ABOUT IT?
I MEAN, REALLY,
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
I'M ONLY DOING THIS BECAUSE
CHIEF ASKED ME TO, SO...
I DON'T EXPECT MUCH
OUT OF THIS RACE EXCEPT
A CHANCE TO KICK BACK AND
PUT SOME DUMBASS POSERS
IN THEIR PLACE.
DON'T THINK FOR A SECOND
I'M GONNA HOLD BACK
JUST BECAUSE I'M
RACING SOME AMATEUR.
WANNA SEE HOW BIG A GAP
THERE IS BETWEEN GUYS LIKE YOU
AND GUYS LIKE ME?
WATCH WHAT I DO
TOMORROW NIGHT.
- THE TRICK WITH THIS COURSE
IS THAT IT COMBINES SEVERAL
DIFFERENT CONDITIONS
PRETTY SEAMLESSLY.
THE CAR AND YOUR TECHNIQUE WILL
HAVE TO BE IN PERFECT BALANCE,
NOTHING LESS THAN YOUR BEST
WILL GET YOU THROUGH.
WE'LL START OUT LIKE WE DID
BEFORE BY KEEPING 80%, ALRIGHT?
THIS ISN'T THE TOUDOU SCHOOL'S
REGULAR COURSE,
BUT KEEP IN MIND
SINCE THEY'VE DRIVEN IT
MORE TIMES THAN WE HAVE,
THE ADVANTAGE IS THEIRS.
SO STAY FOCUSED.
- HE'S ON FIRE TONIGHT.
HOT DAMN.
- YEAH, NO KIDDING.
- KEEP IN MIND THIS ISN'T
THE RACE, SO TAKE IT EASY.
DON'T THINK ABOUT WHETHER YOU'LL
BE THE ONE REPRESENTING US
TOMORROW NIGHT AND JUST TAKE
THE COURSE AT FACE VALUE.
- RIGHT.
- IT'S LIKE I ALWAYS TELL YOU...
YOUR ONLY OPPONENT IS THE ROAD.
- LET'S DO THIS.
- HEY, RYOSUKE...
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
YOU HARDLY EVER SCOUT OUT
THE COURSE FIRST ON YOUR OWN.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
BRINGING THE FC?
I MEAN, C'MON.
- TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
THERE'S NO HIDDEN MEANING
BEHIND MY BRINGING THE FC.
EVERY NOW AND AGAIN
I JUST LIKE TO
FEEL OUT THE COURSE FOR
MYSELF, YOU KNOW?
BUT, THEN AGAIN I...
- WHAT?
- I'M JUST A LITTLE
CONFUSED RIGHT NOW, THAT'S ALL.
FUMIHIRO, I'D LIKE YOU TO TAKE
COMMAND FOR THE NEXT FEW HOURS.
WE'RE JUST GOING THROUGH
THE MOTIONS ANYWAY.
THERE'S SHOULDN'T BE
ANY PROBLEMS.
- BUT, WHY? WHAT WILL YOU
BE DOING IN THE MEANTIME?
- SLEEPING.
- WHAT? WAIT...
- IT JUST HIT ME I HAVEN'T
SLEPT IN LIKE THREE DAYS
THANKS TO THAT
CLINICAL MEDICINE REPORT
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO WRITE.
IT'S A WONDER I WAS ALERT ENOUGH
TO DRIVE HERE IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
HOLD DOWN THE FORT FOR ME, HUH?
- THAT'S WHAT HE MEANS.
THE UPS AND DOWNS
ARE STEEP AS HELL,
AND THE CORNERS ARE
ALL TOO DIFFERENT
TO GET A GOOD RHYTHM GOING.
RYOSUKE WAS RIGHT WHEN HE SAID
NOTHING LESS THAN MY BEST
WILL GET ME THROUGH.
IF I SHOW HIM I'VE GOT
THIS ONE IN THE BAG,
IT'LL MEAN THE CHANCE
TO GO HEAD-TO-HEAD
WITH A BONA FIDE PROFESSIONAL.
YOU BET YOUR ASS
I'M GONNA STAY FOCUSED!
- Fumihiro: I WONDER HOW THIS
IS ALL GOING TO TURN OUT.
TO BE HONEST,
I'M GETTING A LITTLE WORRIED.
- WHAT, YOU? WORRIED? NO WAY.
- DON'T START WITH THAT.
LOOK, SOMETHING IS WRONG,
TRUST ME.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME THE BOSS
HAS PULLED SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
YEAH, WELL...
HE'S PROBABLY ALREADY
MADE UP HIS MIND
NOT TO GO WITH THE 8-6
ON THIS COURSE.
- HMM. I WAS THINKING
THE SAME THING.
WHAT'S GOING ON
IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS, RYOSUKE?
NAH. IT CAN'T BE.
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS. CLOSE HER UP.
- THAT OUGHTA DO IT, MAN.
SHE'S ALL YOURS.
- COOL. THANKS.
- ( engine starting )
- MAN, I'M SORE AS HELL.
SLEEPING IN A CAR DOESN'T DO
WONDERS FOR YOUR BACK
OR YOUR NERVES, EITHER.
- RYOSUKE SURE DIDN'T HAVE ANY
TROUBLE CATCHING UP ON HIS Z'S.
THE MAN'S MORE AT HOME IN A CAR
THAN HE IS IN HIS OWN BED.
( chuckles ) I THINK IT'S SWEET.
- HOW CAN YOU SIT THERE
AND SMILE?
THIS ISN'T FUNNY, MAN.
AFTER LAST NIGHT'S PRACTICE RUN
I UNDERSTAND BETTER THAN EVER
JUST HOW IMPORTANT
RYOSUKE'S PRESENCE
REALLY IS FOR PROJECT D.
HE'S NOT JUST THE BRAINS
BEHIND WHAT WE DO,
HE'S THE INSPIRATION, AND FOR
HIM TO CHECK OUT LIKE THAT MEANS
SOMETHING HAS GOT TO BE
REALLY WRONG.
YOU WERE THERE.
TRY TO TELL ME WE WEREN'T FLYING
BY THE SEAT OF OUR PANTS.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIM TO BE
SO NONCHALANT, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
I HATE TO SAY THIS, BUT
I THINK IT MEANS THE WORST.
DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
KEEP THIS TO YOURSELF, OKAY.
IT'S LIKE THIS...
IT'S JUST THAT...
I FEEL LIKE THE BOSS HAS
BACKED HIMSELF INTO A CORNER
HE CAN'T THINK HIS WAY OUT OF.
WHAT IF HE'S GONE OVER EVERY
POSSIBLE STRATEGY IN HIS HEAD
ONLY TO FIGURE OUT THAT THERE'S
NO WAY WE CAN POSSIBLY WIN?
- Matsumoto: GOOD WORK, GUYS.
TWO HOURS TO SPARE
BEFORE THE RACE
AND ALL THE TWEAKING WE COULDN'T
FINISH LAST NIGHT IS DONE.
NOT BAD, IF
I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
WE MIGHT JUST HAVE A SHOT
AT THIS THING AFTER ALL.
OF COURSE, THAT'S NO REASON
TO GET COCKY.
- HEY! HEADS UP,
THEY'RE HERE!
- LET'S GET A MOVE ON, FELLAS...
GET THOSE LIGHTS UP.
- THEIR BOSS-MAN FINALLY
REARS HIS UGLY HEAD.
I CAN TELL AT A GLANCE WHICH
ONE OF THEM IS HERE TO RACE.
- SO CAN I.
JUST LOOK AT HIM.
HERE WE GO. MOMENT OF TRUTH.
FRONT AND CENTER, YOU TWO.
AFTER LOOKING OVER
THE DATA FROM LAST NIGHT,
I'VE REACHED A DECISION.
AND WE'RE GONNA GO
WITH THE 8-6 TONIGHT.
TAKUMI, YOU'RE UP.
- ( all gasp )
- THIS IS BULLSHIT.
I'M THE ONE WHO CAME OUT AHEAD
ON THE FRIGGIN' PRACTICE RUNS
LAST NIGHT, AREN'T IT?
- CONGRATULATIONS BY THE WAY.
- I'M NOT AGREEING TO THIS
UNTIL YOU EXPLAIN IT TO ME.
WHY THE DAMN 8-6?
- HOW 'BOUT I DRAW YOU
A DIAGRAM AFTER YOU REMEMBER
WHO CALLS THE SHOTS
AROUND HERE?
TAKUMI.
TAKE SHOTGUN. YOU I ARE GONNA
HAVE A LITTLE HEART-TO-HEART.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
- KEISUKE, LOOK...
DON'T LET IT GET TO YOU.
YOUR BROTHER NEVER WOULD
HAVE CHOSEN THE 8-6 TONIGHT
UNLESS THERE WAS
A LOGICAL REASON FOR IT.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING, MAN?
- IS THAT ACTUALLY SUPPOSED
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER?
- OH, GOD.
WHOA.
DUDE, YOU HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT I'D GIVE
TO WEAR THAT THING JUST ONCE.
- YOU IDIOT, THIS IS A
PROFESSIONAL RACING UNIFORM,
NOT A COSTUME.
WEARING THIS REMINDS ME I CAN'T
MESS AROUND OUT THERE TONIGHT,
NOT WHEN MY PROFESSIONAL
REPUTATION IS ON THE LINE.
- YEAH, WELL, I'M JUST GLAD TO
HEAR YOU KNOW WHAT'S AT STAKE.
STAY SHARP. THEIR FD IS NOTHING
TO SNEEZE AT.
KEEP YOUR GUARD UP.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M READY FOR ANYTHING.
IF I'M NOT CAREFUL, THE FD CAN
LOSE ME ON THE STRAIGHTAWAY.
BUT LEAVE IT TO ME, CHIEF, I
KNOW EXACTLY WHAT I NEED TO DO.
- YOU'VE GOT THE 8-6
READY TO GO NOW, RIGHT?
- YEP. WARMED UP
AND READY TO KICK ASS.
ALL SHE'S WAITING ON
IS HER DRIVER.
- THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR.
LET'S DO THIS.
- YES, SIR.
- OKAY. WE'RE READY TO GO.
SINCE THE COURSE HAS
MORE THAN ENOUGH WIDTH,
WE WANTED TO SEE IF YOU WOULDN'T
MIND STARTING OFF SIDE-BY-SIDE
INSTEAD OF HAVING
ONE CAR FOLLOW.
- YEAH, SURE.
WHATEVER. FINE.
- SIDE BY SIDE IT IS.
ALL RIGHT GUYS,
START LINING 'EM UP!
LET'S GO!
- ( engine revving )
- IS THIS SOME KINDA JOKE?
THE 8-6? THAT'S INSANE!
- GOTTA ADMIT, I DIDN'T EXACTLY
SEE THIS ONE COMING.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, BOSS, ARE
THEY ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT?
- ( chuckles ) I THINK
THE BOYS FROM GUNMA
ARE GONNA GIVE US A LITTLE RUN
FOR OUR MONEY.
WE FINE-TUNED THE DEMONSTRATION
CAR UNDER THE ASSUMPTION
IT'D BE UP AGAINST THE FD.
THEIR GOING WITH THE 8-6
WASN'T PART OF THE EQUATION.
SNEAKY BASTARDS.
OF COURSE, THERE'S
ALWAYS THE CHANCE
THEY'RE JUST
UNDERESTIMATING TOMOYUKI.
I DUNNO. EITHER WAY,
I'M THINKIN' THIS LITTLE RACE
IS GONNA BE AN INTERESTING ONE.
- ALL RIGHT!
HERE COMES THE COUNTDOWN!
FIVE. FOUR. THREE.
TWO. ONE. GO!
- WE'RE LEADING!
BY HALF A CAR-LENGTH!
- DON'T LET HIM PASS!
- THEY'RE COMING UP
ON THE CORNER.
WHO'S IT GONNA BE?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )