- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ( cars accelerating )
- ( tires screeching )
- I HEARD THAT D'S
TAKING A BREAK
FROM EXPEDITIONS THIS WEEK.
- YEAH YOU HEARD RIGHT.
REPAIRING KEISUKE'S CAR
IS PROBABLY GOING
TO TAKE ANOTHER WEEK,
MAYBE EVEN A LITTLE BIT
LONGER THAN THAT.
WE FIGURED WE'D TAKE
SOME TIME OFF
TO GIVE EVERYBODY
SOME MUCH NEEDED REST.
- THAT LAST SAITAMA EXPEDITION
MUST'VE BEEN ROUGH ON YOU GUYS.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
DEALING WITH JERKS DUMPING
OIL ALL OVER THE COURSE,
BUSTING UP KEISUKE'S CAR.
- I GUESS IN A COUNTRY THIS SIZE
YOU'RE BOUND TO RUN
INTO A FEW PRICKS
IF YOU TRAVEL LONG ENOUGH.
- Takumi: I GUESS,
BUT I WASN'T EXPECTING THEM TO
TARGET OUR PRACTICE LIKE THAT?
IT MADE ME REALIZE I GOTTA KEEP
MY GUARD UP 24/7.
- YEAH, BUT COME ON, DUDE,
YOU STILL WON.
MAN, YOU'RE A DRIVER
AFTER MY OWN HEART.
IT'S LIKE WINNINGS
A PART OF YOUR NATURE NOW!
THE ONLY THING THAT SURPRISE
ME IS IF YOU WEREN'T FIRST
TO CROSS THE LINE.
- YOU SAY THAT BUT IT'S REALLY
DIFFICULT TO KEEP WINNING
ON COURSES YOU'VE NEVER
EVEN SEEN BEFORE.
NOT TO MENTION ALL THE PRESSURE
THAT COMES ALONG WITH IT.
- THIS LAST BATTLE WE HAD,
IT GAVE ME THE CHANCE TO SEE HOW
INCREDIBLE KEISUKE REALLY IS.
HE NEVER GIVES UP.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW TOUGH
THE SITUATION GETS
OR HOW FAST HIS OPPONENT IS,
NOTHING PULLS HIS CONCENTRATION
OF ATTACKING THE COURSE.
EVEN SOME OF OUR GUYS STARTED
TO THINK IT WAS A LOSS CAUSE,
BUT KEISUKE KEPT PUSHING,
THERE'S AN ENERGY TO HIM,
YOU KNOW. IT'S HARD NOT
TO GET PULLED IN.
WATCHING THAT MADE
ME REALIZE THAT
LOSING IS JUST NOT
AN OPTION FOR ME.
IF YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT
PRESSURE TRY DRIVING FOR THE D.
- ( sighs ) YEAH,
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT.
AFTER ALL PROJECT D HAS
COME THIS FAR
WITHOUT LOSING ONE TIME.
THE PRESSURE ON BOTH OF
YOU MUST BE ENORMOUS.
- I KNOW RIGHT? SERIOUSLY,
WE CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE IT.
- Iketani: YEAH, WAIT,
WHADDYA MEAN "WE"?
- HEY, LONG WAIT?
- MMM-MMM. IT'S WEIRD
SEEING YOU IN THAT FC?
- YEAH WELL, I HAD TO BORROW
MY BROTHERS CAR.
HE USUALLY DOESN'T
LET ME USE IT.
TODAY THOUGH, I TWISTED HIS ARM.
C'MON, HOP ON IN.
- SURE!
- SO, WHERE DO YOU
WANT TO EAT?
I OWE YOU BIG FOR THE
OTHER DAY, SO IT'S YOUR CALL.
WE CAN EVEN TAKE THE
HIGHWAY UP INTO TOKYO,
IF YOU'RE IN THE MOOD.
- YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
BUT I'M NOT ALL THAT CRAZY
ABOUT CROWDED PLACES.
I GUESS I PREFER GUNMA OVER
TOKYO, IF THAT'S COOL BY YOU.
- HEY, IT'S WHATEVER YOU
WANT TO DO.
- I JUST FIGURED IT BE BETTER IF
WE'RE GOING TO BE IN THE CAR.
IF WE'RE IN GUMNA,
WE CAN DRIVE AROUND
AND NOT HAVE TO DEAL WITH TOKYO
TRAFFIC ALL DAY. IS THAT OK?
- SOUNDS GOOD.
WOW! WHAT AN
AMAZING VIEW!
ALL THE CARS LOOK
SO TINY FROM UP HERE.
I WONDER WHERE THE
HIGHWAY ENTRANCE IS.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN
FOR PROJECT D
NOW THAT SAITAMA
EXPEDITION IS OVER?
WHERE ARE YOU GUY'S
HEADED OFF TO NEXT?
- IBARAKI.
- WHOA, THAT'S PRETTY FAR AWAY.
HEY, I WAS WONDERING...
- SUP...
- YOU MIND IF I KEEP
SHOWING UP AT YOUR BATTLES
TO CHEER YOU ON?
IT'S COOL IF YOU WANT TO IGNORE
ME. I GET IT WHY YOU DO THAT.
I JUST LOVE WATCHING YOU DRIVE.
BESIDES, MAYBE I'D
GET THE OPPORTUNITY
TO HELP YOU OUT AGAIN.
I MEAN IT WAS LUCKY I WAS
THERE THE LAST TIME, RIGHT?
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN
YOU MIGHT NEED ME.
- YOU'RE SOMETHING ELSE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
WHEN YOU GET AN IDEA,
I BET IT'S PRETTY POINTLESS
TO TALK YOU OUT OF IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE YOUNG OR WHAT,
BUT WHATEVER IT IS...
I CAN ALREADY TELL
YOU'RE THE TYPE OF PERSON
WHO WOULD TACKLE A CORNER
WITH NO HESITATION,
WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING WHAT'S
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF IT?
- IS THAT A BAD THING?
- NAH, I'M JUST TALKIN'.
YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT IT.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT THAT
AFTER DINNER.
I'M GETTING HUNGRY.
HOW 'BOUT YOU?
- ( phone ringing )
- Fumihiro: HEY, RYOSUKE?
IT'S ME.
I CALLED TO GIVE YOU AN
UPDATE ON THE FD.
IT'S A BIG JOB, BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE WE'RE GONNA BE ABLE TO DO
EVERYTHING WE TALKED
ABOUT FOR HER.
THE WHOLE NINE, I THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT WANT TO KNOW.
- SOUNDS GOOD. I APPRECIATE
THE HELP. THANKS, FUMIHIRO.
- NO SWEAT. HEY I'M JUST
GLAD TO HAVE A HAND IN IT.
IT'S A GREAT EXCUSE TO PULL AN
ALL OUT MODIFICATION,
REALLY MAKE SOME IMPROVEMENTS.
AFTER THIS, YOU WON'T BELIEVE
WHAT THE FD WILL BE CAPABLE OF.
- THAT'S GOOD. CAUSE WE GOT SOME
DIFFICULT BATTLES COMING UP.
SO WE NEED TO LIGHTEN THE
LOAD ON THE DRIVERS
AS MUCH AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
- I WAS ACTUALLY PLANNING
ON TAKING KENTA
AND CHECKING OUT THE NEXT
COURSE TOMORROW.
GET AN IDEA OF WHAT
THE GUYS WILL BE UP AGAINST.
- PERFECT, JUST BE
CAREFUL OUT THERE, OKAY?
- GOT IT. I'LL CALL YOU
LATER ON.
- THIS DOESN'T FEEL REAL.
TO EVERYONE ELSE HERE,
I'M SURE WE LOOK LIKE
A NORMAL EVERYDAY LOVING COUPLE
OUT ON A ROMANTIC DATE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN THIS HAPPY.
MY HEART IS BEATING SO FAST,
IT FEELS LIKE A TACHOMETER
WITH THE NEEDLE PUSHED UP
ALL THE WAY IN THE RED.
I GUESS THIS IS WHAT IT
FEELS LIKE TO SIT ACROSS
FROM YOUR SOUL MATE.
I NEVER THOUGHT I COULD FEEL
THIS WAY ABOUT SOMEONE.
I DON'T EVER WANT THIS
NIGHT TO END.
AMAZING.
DRIVING AKAGI'S IN THE PASSENGER
SEAT OF MY DARLING'S CAR.
HE'S DRIVING CASUALLY
LIKE HE'S ON AUTO PILOT.
BUT I CAN TELL THE DIFFERENCE.
EVERY TURN IS ULTRA SMOOTH.
HIS TECHNIQUE IS SO ADVANCED
THAT EVEN DRIVING THE SPEED
LIMIT IS AN EXPERIENCE.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
THERE'S NO CHANGE IN MOMENTUM
WHEN HE UP SHIFTS.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE IT'S
SECOND NATURE TO HIM.
HE MANIPULATES THE
CLUTCH SO DELICATELY,
AND YET HE'S STILL IN COMPLETE
COMMAND OF THE ROAD.
IF THERE'S SUCH A THING AS
PERFECT TECHNIQUE,
THIS MIGHT BE IT.
YOUR DRIVING IS
UNBELIEVABLE, KEISUKE.
- YOU THINK SO?
I WASN'T EVEN REALLY TRYING.
- THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT
SO KILLER.
YOU FINESSE YOUR WAY BETWEEN
THE CLUTCH AND THE GEAR BOX
LIKE IT'S NOTHING.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THAT BEFORE.
- WELL, IT ISN'T LIKE THAT
ALL THE TIME.
JUST BE GLAD THAT I WASN'T
DRIVING LIKE I DO
IN THE MIDDLE OF A RACE,
I CAN BE A LITTLE ROUGH
ON THE CLUTCH.
CONSTANTLY PUSHING A CAR
ALL THE WAY TO ITS LIMITS
WHEN WE'RE ON EXPEDITIONS,
ADDS A LOT OF STRESS
AND A LOT OF WEAR AND TEAR,
SO WHEN I'M DRIVING OR OFF PEAK
I LIKE TO TRY AND BABY HER
AS MUCH AS I CAN.
- Man: HEY!
CHECK IT OUT, MAN, IT'S KEISUKE.
- WHAT THE HECK ARE
YOU DOING OUT HERE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU ON A DATE.
- YEAH, WHO THE HOTTIE?
IS THAT YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
- WHY DON'T YOU GUY'S SHUT THE
HELL UP. IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
NOW GET OUTTA HERE!
- ( both giggling )
- DON'T MIND THEM. JUST A COUPLE
OF PRICKS I USE TO HANG WITH.
I WASN'T IN THE BEST CROWD
BEFORE I STARTED DRIVING.
I USED TO GET INTO FIGHTS ALL
THE TIME
AND CAUSE ALL KINDS OF PROBLEMS
WITH MY PARENTS AND AT SCHOOL.
IT SOUNDS STUPID WHEN
I TALK ABOUT IT NOW,
BUT BACK THEN,
I DIDN'T HAVE ANY DIRECTION.
I WAS ALWAYS FELT BORED
AND ANGRY
AND DON'T KNOW I GUESS
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO HANDLE IT.
- I KNOW THAT FEELING
VERY WELL.
- AFTER A WHILE IT SEEMS LIKE MY
PARENTS HAD GIVEN UP ON ME.
BUT MY BROTHER UNDERSTOOD
WHAT I WAS GOING THROUGH.
WHENEVER I LOOK AT THIS BABY,
IT TAKES ME BACK TO THE FIRST
TIME HE GOT ME IN THIS FC
AND BROUGHT ME OUT
TO MOUNT AKAGI.
AS SOON AS WE HIT THE DOWNHILL
HE WENT ALL OUT.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE
I WAS FREAKIN' TERRIFIED.
I SERIOUSLY THOUGHT
WE WERE DEAD.
AT THAT POINT I STARTED
TO THINK HE HAD PLANS
TO TAKE HIS DELINQUENT
BROTHER OUT
ON SOME KIND OF
DOUBLE SUICIDE RUN.
- ( chuckles )
- THAT WAS THREE YEARS AGO.
AND I STILL HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO BEAT MY BROTHER'S
DOWNHILL TIME FROM BACK THEN,
NOT FROM LACK OF TRYING.
- WHAT? NO WAY!
YOU DON'T STILL THINK RYOSUKE
IS THAT MUCH BETTER THAN YOU,
DO YOU?
- WELL, YEAH. BUT EITHER WAY MY
BROTHER TURNED MY LIFE AROUND
FOR THE BETTER THAT NIGHT.
I'D HATE TO THINK WHAT I
WOULD HAVE ENDED UP LIKE
IF I WASN'T ABLE TO DRIVE.
- WOW.
- AND SO, GOING BACK TO WHAT WE
WERE TALKING ABOUT EARLIER.
I GOT TO BE COMPLETELY
HONEST WITH YOU.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I JUST CAN'T DATE
ANYONE RIGHT NOW.
- ( gasps )
- PLEASE DON'T COME
SEE ME ANYMORE.
- ( stutters ) I...
EVEN FROM THE START,
I DIDN'T REALLY EXPECT THAT
YOU'D WANT TO DATE ME.
YOU DON'T FEEL ABOUT ME
HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
I ONLY COME AROUND
BECAUSE I WANT TO.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE THAT CAME FROM.
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU SUDDENLY
DECIDE TO BE SO COLD TO ME?
AFTER BEING SO SWEET
TO ME ALL DAY.
YOU TOOK ME DRIVING,
WE HAD A NICE DINNER,
AND YOU EVEN OPENED UP TO ME.
OR I THOUGHT YOU DID.
YOU MADE ME FEEL LIKE WE WERE
MAKING A CONNECTION
AND THAT MAYBE WE COULD
HAVE A CHANCE TO BE TOGETHER,
THEN YOU DROP THIS?
- I KNOW AND IT'S NOT LIKE
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
BUT I'VE DECIDED THAT I'VE ONLY
GOT ENOUGH TIME AND ENERGY
TO REALLY CONCENTRATE ON
ONE THING AND FOR RIGHT NOW
THAT THING IS PROJECT D.
IF I ALLOW MYSELF TO
BE DISTRACTED
BY EVEN ONE OTHER THING,
THEN I WON'T BE ABLE TO
PUT EVERYTHING I'VE GOT
INTO DRIVING FOR PROJECT D.
I CAN'T LET THAT HAPPEN
- BUT I UNDERSTAND THAT!
I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
PROJECT D IS TO YOU!
I'VE ALWAYS TRIED TO
KEEP MY DISTANCE
AND NOT GET IN YOUR WAY!
BUT THAT'S STILL ISN'T
GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO
COME AROUND AT ALL?
- IT'S FOR THE BEST. AND CRYING
WON'T CHANGE MY MIND.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND HOW YOU JUST
WATCHING WOULD BE GOOD ENOUGH.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT WHEN YOU
FALL IN LOVE WITH SOMEONE,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO GIVE THEM
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE TO GIVE.
IT WOULD MAKE ME FEEL
ABSOLUTELY MISERABLE
TO BE IN SUCH A
ONE SIDED RELATIONSHIP.
I WOULDN'T BE OK WITH THAT.
AND NEITHER WOULD YOU.
I'M SURPRISED YOU HAVEN'T
REALIZED THAT YOURSELF.
YOU AND ME AREN'T THE KIND OF
PEOPLE WHO CAN DO ANYTHING
IN OUR LIVES HALF WAY.
AS WE GET INTO THE SUMMER
OUR EXPEDITIONS
WILL BECOME TOUGHER AND TOUGHER,
AND I JUST WON'T HAVE THE TIME
TO COMMIT TO A GIRLFRIEND.
YOU GET WORN DOWN,
YOU START TO BLAME ME,
THAT'S JUST HOW IT'LL PLAY OUT.
I LIKE YOU AND I THINK
YOU'RE A REALLY BEAUTIFUL GIRL.
BUT YOU AND I ARE
NEVER GOING TO WORK.
- ( sobbing )
- IT'S BETTER WE STOP THIS NOW.
- ( crying )
I WANT TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
ONE FAVOR AND
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE.
JUST LET ME SIT IN
YOUR PASSENGER SEAT
AND TAKE ME DRIVING
AT FULL SPEED!
PLEASE!
- OKAY.
- JUST LIKE I THOUGHT,
HE IS AMAZING!
IT'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT
FROM EARLIER.
I KNOW HE WAS GOOD,
BUT THIS IS UNREAL.
COULD THIS REALLY BE
THE END?
AM I REALLY NEVER
GOING TO SEE MY BABY AGAIN?
I DON'T WANT THAT.
HE'S THE MOST AMAZING
MAN I'VE EVER MET.
I WISH HE WANTED WHAT I WANT.
I DON'T I'LL EVER FALL IN
LOVE AGAIN. HOW COULD I?
I'LL NEVER MEET ANYONE AS
PERFECT AS MY DARLING.
NOT AS LONG AS I LIVE.
( crying )
- ♪ HERE WE ARE ♪
♪ WE KISS AND PASS THE RED LIGHT
AND DRIVE IN AFFECTION ♪
♪ BLESS TO BE HERE ♪
♪ WE DREAM RIGHT BY YOUR SIDE
IN EACH DIRECTION ♪
♪ GUYS CALL IT TIGER ♪
♪ GIRLS CALL IT SUGAR ♪
- ( car approaching )
- ( tires screeching )
- Yuuichi: HOW HAS TAKUMI
BEEN DOING SINCE THEN?
WHAT DO YOU THINK, IS
HE GOING TO FIND A WAY
TO PULL OUT OF THIS SLUMP?
- NO WAY TO TELL YET.
BUT I WILL SAY THAT IT
LOOKS LIKE HE'S HEADED
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
I'M STARTING TO SEE A WHOLE
DIFFERENT LOOK IN HIS EYES NOW
WHEN HE GETS OUT OF THE CAR
AFTER A DELIVERY.
- OH YEAH?
- IT'S GETTING PRETTY OBVIOUS.
HE'S BECOME INVOLVED
IN A HUGE BATTLE,
AND HE RACES ON THE STREETS OF
AKINA'S DOWNHILL EVERY MORNING.
- HUH? AGAINST WHO?
- HE'S RACES AGAINST HIMSELF.
- HOLD ON, DID YOU JUST
SAY HIMSELF?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
WHEN HE'S DRIVING
THE EIGHT-SIX,
HE'S DESPERATELY CHASING
AFTER THE IMAGINARY IMPREZA
THAT HE SEE'S IN FRONT OF HIM.
WHEN HE'S IN THE IMPREZA,
IT'S THE OPPOSITE
AND HE'S PUTTING DISTANCE
BETWEEN HIMSELF
AND THE EIGHT-SIX RUNNING
HIM DOWN, SEE.
- I SEE.
- SINCE HE KNOWS EVERYTHING
THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT THE COURSE,
IT SHOULD BE EASY FOR HIM
TO SPOT THE DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN THE TWO CARS.
THINGS LIKE THE
DIFFERENCE IN SPEED
FROM ONE CORNER TO ANOTHER.
- IT SOUNDS COMPLEX, BUT WITH
TAKUMI, YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
- BY NOW AFTER HAVING BEEN
BEHIND THE WHEEL OF BOTH CARS
HE SHOULD HAVE A PRETTY ACCURATE
IDEA OF HOW MANY SECONDS
AND HOW MANY METERS
THERE WOULD BE BETWEEN THEM
IF THEY WERE BATTLING IT OUT
ON A RELATIVELY LONG STRETCH.
IF TAKUMI IS ANYTHING
LIKE ME,
I'M BETTING HE CAN
SEE THE IMPREZA
THROUGH THE EIGHT-SIX'S
FRONT WINDSHIELD
AS CLEARLY AS IF
IT WERE REALLY THERE.
- ( panting ) SO HOT!
I GUESS IT MEANS SUMMERS
FINALLY HERE.
- IT WAS RIGHT AROUND
THIS TIME LAST YEAR
WHEN WE HAD THAT
ACQUAINTANCE BATTLE
AGAINST THE RED SUNS,
WASN'T IT?
- I THINK YOUR RIGHT.
- EVERYTHING ABOUT THE DOWNHILL
LEGEND OF AKINA'S EIGHT-SIX,
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT IT
ALL THAT STARTED LAST SUMMER.
- NO QUESTION THIS YEAR SURE
WENT BY IN A FLASH.
IT'S TRULY HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
TAKUMI REALLY ROSE TO THE RANKS
TO BECOME A LIVING LEGEND
AND JUST IN A YEAR.
- YEAH IT WASN'T THAT LONG AGO
HE WAS PUMPING GAS.
- ( groans )
- AND ALL OF THE SUDDEN, I AM
HORRIBLY, HORRIBLY DEPRESSED.
- YOU KNOW WHAT WE NEED,
CHICKS, MAN.
IT'S NOT RIGHT FOR
TWO STUDS LIKE US
TO BE SINGLE FOR THE SUMMER!
SOMEBODY TAKE ME!
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW PROFESSIONAL
DRIVERS THAT WILL PUT THEMSELVES
THROUGH THAT KIND OF
ROUTINE EVERY DAY.
IF HE'S PUTTING THAT MUCH TIME
INTO PRACTICE
HE'S BOUND TO HAVE MADE
SOME STRIDES IN FIGURING OUT
HOW TO KEEP UP WITH THE IMPREZA
AND THE EIGHT-SIX BY NOW.
- YOU WOULD THINK SO, HUH.
- YEAH.
- HMM, I USUALLY WOULD TOO, BUT
YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT IT THIS WAY.
IMAGINE THAT DURING ONE OF THESE
BATTLES TAKUMI MAKES A DISCOVERY
WHILE HE'S DRIVING
THE EIGHT-SIX.
THIS DISCOVERY SHOWS HIM
A NEW LINE TO TAKE
THAT WILL SHORTEN HIS TIME
BY A FRACTION OF A SECOND.
BUT THE VERY NEXT DAY,
THE IMPREZA WILL START DRIVING
ON THAT EXACT SAME LINE.
- HMM, YEAH, THAT'S GOTTA BE
TOUGH ON HIM.
YOU KNOW I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE HE'S
CHASING AN OPPONENT
THAT HE'LL NEVER CATCH UP TO.
- UNTIL NOW ALL HIS SKILLS HAVE
COME FROM HIS UNDERSTANDING
OF ONE KIND OF CAR,
BUT AS HE IMPROVES
HE'S LEARNING THE VALUE
OF KNOWING ALL YOU CAN ABOUT THE
CAR YOUR OPPONENT DRIVES.
IN A NUT SHELL, TAKUMI'S
WHOLE OUTLOOK
ON DRIVING AND TECHNIQUE
ARE CHANGING.
LET ME PUT IT THIS WAY,
YOU KNOW HOW THERE ARE
AN INFINITE NUMBER OF POINTS
IN A LINE THAT
CONNECTS TWO POINTS?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S WHAT HE'S
BEGINNING TO SEE.
HE'LL PROBABLY START PICKING UP
ON ALL SORTS OF THINGS
HE COULDN'T BEFORE.
EVENTUALLY HIS
EXPERIENCE WILL IMPROVE
HIS CONFIDENCE AND TECHNIQUE.
THAT'S HOW HE'S GOT
THIS FAR AFTER ALL.
AND THAT'S HOW HE'LL CONTINUE.
- ( car accelerating )
- THIS IS SO AWESOME!
WITH THESE MODIFICATIONS,
I'LL NEVER LOSE TO A LAN
EVO OR A GT-R!
- THIS IS AMAZING.
AFTER ALL THE CHANGES
WE MADE TO THE FD,
ITS POWER OUTPUT AND SUSPENSION
ARE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
HE SHOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
CONTROL IT SO WELL,
AT LEAST NOT THIS FAST.
MUST BE THE ACCELERATION
TECHNIQUE HE'S BEEN WORKING ON.
MAN, HE'S GOTTEN GOOD.
- THIS IS PERFECT, YOU CAN
REALLY FEEL THE HORSEPOWER.
BUT IT'S STILL JUST AS
EASY TO DRIVE
BECAUSE THE
TORQUE STAYS HIGH
FROM ALL THE MID RANGE REVVING.
ITS HANDLING ON HIGH SPEED
CORNERS IS PRETTY GOOD TOO.
IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE
OF THE WIDE BODY,
BUT I BET THIS SPOILER HELPS.
THE BEST PART IS THAT IT'S
REALLY STABLE IN CORNERS NOW
WHERE I COULDN'T EVEN STEP ON
THE GAS BEFORE.
I SWEAR, I FEEL LIKE I'M
READY FOR ANYTHING.
MAN, NOBODY CAN
COMPETE WITH THIS RIDE.
- WELL THEN, I GUESS THIS IS
PERFECT TIMING.
WHAT RYOSUKE'S TOLD
ME OUR NEXT OPPONENT
IS APPARENTLY OUR
TOUGHEST ONE TO DATE.
- YEAH? EVEN TOUGHER THAN
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL?
- THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHO
I'M GOING UP AGAINST NEXT.
I'VE BEEN THINKING LATELY
THAT IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE FOUND AN OPPONENT THAT'S
WORTHY OF A REAL BATTLE.
THE SAITAMA AREA TURNED OUT
TO BE A LOT LESS COMPETITIVE
THAN I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT,
IT WAS KIND OF A LETDOWN.
ALTHOUGH WHEN YOU REALLY
STOP TO THINK ABOUT IT,
IT TURNED OUT TO BE
KIND OF A GOOD THING.
IT WAS A CHANCE FOR ME TO
FOCUS ON DRIVING
WITHOUT ALL THE PRESSURE
WE USUALLY DEAL WITH.
- YOU KNOW YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
SEEMS LIKE EVERY RACE WE'VE
HAD AROUND HERE LATELY
HAS TAUGHT YOU ONE
THING OR ANOTHER.
I'M JUST GLAD YOUR
FINDING SOMETHING
TO TAKE AWAY FROM EACH ONE.
DRIVING WITH YOU TODAY
HAS SHOWN ME
HOW MUCH YOU'VE
ALREADY IMPROVED.
I'M IMPRESSED.
- THANKS DUDE. I'M STARTING
TO NOTICE A LITTLE BIT TOO.
THE RACE IN SITAMA MIGHT HAVE
NOT BEEN OUR MOST EXCITING
BATTLE BUT I SURE LEARNED A LOT.
I'M NEVER GONNA FORGET IT.
- THAT'S GOOD. IT'S THE BEST
POSSIBLE OUTLOOK.
- HEY, FUMIHIRO.
- YEAH.
- I WAS WONDERING, YOU THINK MY
BROTHER PICKS THE LOCATIONS
OF PROJECT D'S BATTLES WITH
ALL THIS IN MIND?
- PROBABLY.
ALL OF RYOSUKE'S
DECISIONS SEEM TO HAVE
SOME KIND MEANING TO THEM.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S BECAUSE
COMPARED TO HIM
HE SEES TAKUMI AND ME AS JUST
AS A COUPLE OF AMATEURS?
- NAH, I DON'T THINK SO,
WHAT, DO YOU?
- GUESS NOT.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT AND IF YOU
EVER TELL HIM I'LL DENY IT,
BUT I HAVE AN AMAZING
OLDER BROTHER.
THE NEXT EXPEDITION IS IN
IBARAKI RIGHT?
- WE WENT YESTERDAY,
CHECKED IT OUT.
- I FEEL LIKE I CAN'T LOSE
NO MATTER WHO I RACE.
AND WITH THIS, I CAN SHOW
MY BROTHER A RACE
THAT WILL SURPRISE EVEN HIM.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
- ♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪