- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ( groaning ) MAN, IT'S SOAKIN'
RIGHT THROUGH.
- HEY REMIND ME AGAIN
WHAT WE'RE DOING
ONCE THE NEWSPAPERS ARE USED UP?
- BUNCH 'EM TOGETHER. WE'LL BURN
THEM IN A FIELD OR SOMETHING.
WHATEVER'S LEFT OF THE OIL
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO GO AT
WITH GOOD OL' FASHIONED WATER,
I GUESS.
WE'LL GET A BUCKET RELAY GOIN'
BETWEEN HERE AND THE RIVER.
'COURSE EVEN THEN, THE SLICK
WON'T WASH AWAY COMPLETELY.
- MAYBE NOT, BUT THE
FIRST GOOD RAINSTORM
THAT BLOWS THROUGH OUTTA TAKE
CARE OF THE REST.
( sighing )
- ( vehicle approaching )
- HEY.
- ANYTHING WE CAN DO
TO LIGHTEN THE LOAD?
HUH. WHERE KENTA RUN OFF TO?
- HE WENT INTO TOWN
TO PICK UP SOME PARTS.
WE'RE BASICALLY JUST
HAMMERING OUT THE DENTS
WHILE WAITIN' ON
HIM TO GET BACK.
- ( car approaching )
- WHAT? YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDIN'
ME. WHAT'S HE STILL DOING AWAKE?
- WHAT'S UP GUYS?
I THOUGHT I'D STOP BY TO SEE
IF YOU NEEDED ANY HELP.
- DUDE, THANKS,
BUT NO THANKS, REALLY.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU EVEN
DOING HERE?
YOU SHOULD BE RESTING UP
FOR THE BIG RACE TONIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU
SHOULD BE FOCUSING ON.
- YEAH, BUT...
- ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'M GONNA SAY
THIS TO ALL OF YOU.
I'M A REALIST. I KNOW
MY CHANCES OUT THERE
ARE SLIM TO NONE,
WHATEVER WE DO.
STILL, DON'T THINK THAT I'M
GONNA TAKE THAT LYING DOWN.
I HAD MY HEAD UP MY ASS
AND BECAUSE OF IT PROJECT
D'S REP IS ON THE LINE.
THIS IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
SO WHATEVER THE HELL IT TAKES,
I AM GONNA RACE TONIGHT.
- ( engine revving )
- FOR NOW, THE NAME OF THE
GAME IS "PACE YOURSELF".
PROMISE ME YOU WON'T DO
ANYTHING CRAZY, OKAY?
- PROMISE.
- THOSE RIGHT-HAND CORNERS
ARE GONNA BE MURDER
ON YOUR LEFT FRONT SIDE,
SO IT'S IMPORTANT TO TAKE 'EM AS
GENTLY AS POSSIBLE. YOU GOT ME?
- I GOT YOU, DUDE. ALL RIGHT.
I'M OUT OF HERE , PEACE.
COME ON, BABY.
SHOW ME WHATCHA GOT.
FOR THE SAKE OF EVERYONE WHO
LOST SLEEP TRYIN' TO FIX YOU.
FOR THE SAKE OF MY PRIDE,
SHOW ME A MIRACLE!
- ( people laughing )
- THOSE JERK WADS' FACES
WERE PALER'N MY ASS.
AND MR. PRETTY BOY WITH HIS
PRECIOUS SPIKED HAIR
LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
ABOUT READY TO RUN HOME
AND CRY TO HIS MOMMA!
OH, HE MIGHT TALK A BIG GAME,
BUT WHEN THE CHIPS ARE DOWN,
MAN'S GOT NOTHING TO
PONY UP WITH.
- IF WE CAN MANAGE TO INTIMIDATE
THE EIGHT SIX'S DRIVER
HALF AS EASILY AS THE FD'S,
THEN I'D SAY WE HAVE THIS RACE
PRETTY MUCH IN THE BAG.
- IN THE BAG AND
OVER OUR SHOULDER.
- ( all laughing )
- ( tires screeching )
- THERE'S A WEIRD VIBRATION
WHEN I BRAKE AT THIS SPEED,
BUT LOOKS LIKE SHE CAN STILL
HANDLE THE LEFT-HAND CORNERS
THE WAY SHE ALWAYS DOES.
THE RIGHT-HANDERS, THOUGH,
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT HAVE
GOT ME WORRIED.
LET'S SEE IF ALL THAT
ELBOW GREASE WAS FOR NOTHING.
DAMMIT!
- ( tires screeching )
- ( breathing heavily )
SON OF A BITCH!
- ( honking )
- I WAS ONLY DRIVIN' HER AT
EIGHTY PERCENT,
BUT THE MOMENT I SHIFTED THE
WEIGHT TO THE LEFT FRONT SIDE,
FRIGGIN' THING SPUN LIKE A TOP.
IT'S HOPELESS!
AND HERE I WAS THINKIN' I COULD
MAKE THIS WORK. WHAT A DUMBASS.
WHAT THE HELL AM I GONNA DO?
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO
FACE THE GUYS AGAIN.
SORRY, BRO. I GUESS
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR PUTTIN'
YOUR FAITH IN ME.
- ( car approaching )
- OH, GREAT. COMPANY.
HOLD ON A SECOND. I KNOW THAT
SOUND. THAT'S A ROTARY ENGINE.
- HEY STRANGER! MIND IF I
CHEER YOU GUYS ON TONIGHT?
WHY ARE YOU PARKED
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
( stuttering )
I MEAN...
( gasping ) OH, GOD.
I KNEW IT. HE'S UPSET!
HE PROBABLY THINKS I'M STALKING
HIM. MAN I BLEW IT!
- LISTEN TO ME. THIS IS
IMPORTANT. DO YOU TRUST ME?
I KNOW EVEN AS FAR
BACK AS WHEN
WE CALLED OURSELVES
THE RED SUNS,
THE WHOLE IDEA OF
COMPETING IN A BORROWED CAR
HAS BEEN STRICTLY FORBIDDEN.
I'VE ALWAYS ACCEPTED THAT,
BUT IT'S JUST NOT GOING TO
WORK FOR ME TONIGHT.
AND I DON'T CARE IF YOU
GET THAT OR NOT, BRO.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT, FINE.
THIS RACE DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
A LEGIT D BATTLE.
BUT I'LL BE DAMNED.
I WILL BE DAMNED IF YOU DON'T
LET ME GET OUR DIGNITY BACK!
- ( sighing )
- IT'S ME, RYOSUKE.
I KNOW THIS IS KINDA LATE,
BUT WE WON'T BE NEEDING
THAT CAR AFTER ALL.
YEAH. THAT'S RIGHT.
MY APOLOGIES.
I'LL CALL YOU LATER, OKAY?
- HANG ON. WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU LET ME GO ON
AND ON LIKE THAT
AND YOU'D ALREADY MADE
ARRANGEMENTS FOR ANOTHER CAR
TO BE BROUGHT HERE TONIGHT?
- IT'S NOT LIKE I WANTED TO BUT
WHAT CHOICE DID WE HAVE?
WHEN YOU BACKS AGAINST THE WALL
YOU DO WHAT YOU GOTTA.
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO INTENTION
OF COMPROMISING
PROJECT D'S WINNING
STREAK BY DEFAULT.
ESPECIALLY IF IT MEANS
CONCEDING TO THEM.
- ( gasping )
- YEAH!
- YEAH, THAT'S ALL
WELL AND GOOD,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK THESE
GUYS ARE GONNA OBJECT
TO OUR SWITCHING CARS LIKE THIS?
I MEAN, C'MON, YOU KNOW ANY
LITTLE THING THEY THINK
MIGHT GIVE US AN ADVANTAGE WILL
JUST BE FLAT-OUT REFUSED.
WE'RE TALKIN' ABOUT USING A
CAR THEY HADN'T EVEN COUNTED ON
RACING IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THERE'S NO WAY ARE THEY GONNA
LET US SLIP BY WITH THAT.
IT'S FUNNY YOU SHOULD BRING THAT
UP, 'CAUSE I HAVE A JOB FOR YOU.
IT'S GONNA REQUIRE JUST A
LITTLE BIT OF SWEET-TALKING
ON YOUR PART, AND A HELLUVA
LOT OF AGGRESSION.
- COME OFF IT MAN.
DON'T TRY TO SELL ME
IT'S THE SAME MODEL LINE,
IT'S A TOTALLY DIFFERENT CAR.
GIMME A BREAK. I MEAN,
WHAT DO WE LOOK LIKE TO YOU,
A COUPLE OF CHUMPS?
- NO, NOT AT ALL. I GUESS,
I'M JUST KINDA SURPRISED
TO SEE YOU TAKING IT SO HARD,
GIVEN HOW EAGER YOU WERE
FOR US TO REPLACE THE FD
WITH THE EIGHT SIX.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
BLABBING ABOUT?
WE NEVER SAID
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- ISN'T THE EIGHT SIX THE SAME
MODEL TRAINING CAR THEY USE
IN F1 RACING?
COME NOW, GENTLEMEN, LET'S
NOT BE DIFFICULT ABOUT THIS.
THINK ABOUT IT. HE'LL STILL BE
DRIVING A BORROWED CAR
HE'S NEVER DRIVEN.
I'D SAY THAT GIVES YOU
THE ADVANTAGE, IF ANYTHING.
IF THAT ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH, THEN
I'M AFRAID OUR HANDS ARE TIED.
WE'LL HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO
POSTPONE TONIGHT'S RACE.
WHICH WILL JUST GIVE US THAT
MUCH MORE TIME TO PRACTICE.
- WELL THEN I'M ASSUMING IT'S
ALL RIGHT WITH THE TWO OF YOU
IF WE JUST PACK UP NOW AND
HEAD BACK TO GUNMA?
- ( both sighing )
- ( motor running )
- WHADYA KNOW. I GAVE 'EM THE
HARD-LINE COLD AS ICE
JUST LIKE YOU SAID, AND
THEY FELL FOR IT.
I FIGURE THEY'VE GOT MORE RIDING
ON TONIGHT'S RACE
THAN THEY'RE LETTING ON.
THEY MAY ACT LIKE
THEY'RE MORE OR LESS
BEING FORCED INTO RACING US,
BUT THE LOOK IN THEIR EYES
TELLS ME A VERY DIFFERENT STORY.
- WOW, YOU DON'T
MISS A BEAT, DO YOU?
SOMETHING HANGS IN THE BALANCE
FOR THEM OVER THIS,
BUT IT ISN'T THEIR PRIDE.
NOT EVEN BRAGGING RIGHTS,
WHICH MUST MEAN
THERE'S SOMETHING
FAR MORE INSIDIOUSLY SPECIFIC.
- ( gasping )
WAIT ARE YOU SAYING
IT'S ABOUT MONEY?
- MOST LIKELY.
- THOSE BASTARDS. THAT'S
WHAT THEY'RE TRYING TO PULL?
NOW WE REALLY GOT TO
CREAM THESE GUYS!
- GOOD LUCK TONIGHT,
PRETTY BOY.
- HUH.
- YOU'LL NEED IT IF
YOU'RE SO DESPERATE
YOU GOTTA BORROW
SOMEONE ELSE'S CAR.
MAN OH MAN, SOME PEOPLE
JUST HAVE NO SHAME.
- HE'S AN ASSHOLE, KEISUKE.
TRY TO IGNORE HIM.
HE'S ONLY TRYING TO
MESS WITH YOUR HEAD.
- TRUST ME, IT'S COOL.
YOU THINK A CHEAP SHOT
LIKE THAT'S GONNA MAKE ME
FORGET HOW LUCKY
I AM TO BE HERE?
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, GUYS,
RIGHT NOW THERE'S NOT A DAMN
THING ANYBODY COULD SAY
THAT WOULD MAKE ME FEEL
ANYTHING BUT GRATITUDE.
WHERE WOULD I BE
WITHOUT THIS TEAM?
WITHOUT THESE GUYS.
WITHOUT HER.
- LET'S DO THIS THING!
IN FIVE, FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE. GO!
- THE PORCUPINE CAN WATCH MY
TAIL LIGHTS GET SMALLER
WHILE HE'S BUSY FEELIN' OUT
HIS NEW RIDE.
THAT'S WHY I CHOSE TO LEAD.
HELL, I'M NOT STUPID. I'M IN
THIS FOR THE SUREFIRE WIN.
- SO, RYOSUKE, THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO ASK YOU ABOUT.
I MEAN, YOU ALREADY HAD A
REPLACEMENT CAR EN ROUTE
WHEN YOU DECIDED TO LET KEISUKE
GO WITH THE GIRL'S FD.
IT WAS THE RIGHT CALL TO MAKE
BUT IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM YOUR
CHARACTER FOR YOU
TO CHANGE YOUR MIND
SO ARBITRARILY.
- WHAT'VE I TOLD YOU ABOUT
JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS?
MAYBE WHEN THE OPPORTUNITY
PRESENTED ITSELF,
I SIMPLY THOUGHT IT BEST
FOR KEISUKE TO FIX THE SITUATION
ON HIS OWN TERMS.
BASED ON HIS OWN EXPERIENCE.
- OF COURSE! HE'S ALREADY
FAMILIAR WITH KYOKO'S CAR
FROM WHEN THE TWO OF THEM RACED!
- AND HENCE MY DECISION.
HE'S GOTTEN A CLOSE LOOK
AT HOW THAT VEHICLE
OPERATES AT ITS LIMITS,
AND PERHAPS MORE IMPORTANTLY,
HOW IT DIFFERS FROM HIS OWN FD.
MY CHOICES MAY SEEM
ARBITRARY SOMETIMES,
BUT IN THE END I'M
AN OPPORTUNIST.
WHENEVER I SEE SOMETHING THAT
INCREASES OUR CHANCES
OF WINNING, I JUMP ON IT.
I'LL ADMIT, THOUGH, IT WAS
DAMN LUCKY FOR US
THAT THAT GIRL SHOWED
UP HERE TONIGHT.
KEISUKE OWES HER ONE.
WE ALL DO.
- AWESOME! JUST LIKE I THOUGHT.
THIS BABY'S GOT POWER AND
A KILLER SUSPENSION SYSTEM.
THANKS, KYOKO,
THIS IS ONE HELL OF A RIDE!
- OKAY, I'VE GOTTA ASK,
ARE YOU FEELIN' ALRIGHT?
I NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS
THOUGHT I'D SEE YOU LET
SOMEONE ELSE BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF THAT THING.
- I HATE TO AGREE
WITH HIM, KYOKO,
BUT YOU HAVE TO KNOW
BY NOW YOUR OBSESSION
WITH THAT CAR IS RATHER
SOMETHING OF A LOCAL LEGEND.
- I AM SURPRISED AT MYSELF.
IF ANYONE HAD TOLD ME EVEN A
FEW WEEKS AGO
THAT I'D BE LETTING SOMEONE
BORROW MY PRIDE AND JOY,
I'D HAVE TOLD THEM TO GET
THEIR HEAD EXAMINED.
BUT RIGHT NOW I COULDN'T BE
HAPPIER TO HELP KEISUKE OUT.
I MEAN, IT'S KINDA LIKE TONIGHT
WAS JUST DESTINED TO BE.
IF LENDING HIM MY CAR
WILL HELP MY DARLING,
YOU BETTER BELIEVE I'LL DO IT.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING
I WOULDN'T DO FOR HIM.
I'M ROOTING FOR YOU, BABE,
JUST LIKE I SAID I WOULD.
DON'T YOU DARE LOSE THIS!
- ( tires screeching )
- HOLY CRAP! ARE YOU SEEIN' THE
SLIDE CONTROL THAT DUDE'S GOT?
- THAT'S NOT EVEN HIS OWN CAR,
MAN, HE HAD TO GET IT ON LOAN.
IF THIS KEISUKE'S NOT AN FD
SPECIALIST I SURE AS HELL
DON'T KNOW WHAT ONE LOOKS LIKE.
- DON'T GET YOU PANTIES IN A WAD
YET, HE'S STILL GETTIN' DUSTED.
THIS IS GONNA BE A TOUGH ONE.
WORD ON THE STREET IS THAT GUY
DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE TO
RUN THE COURSE AT ALL
LAST NIGHT, NOT EVEN ONE.
- HE'S RACING A LAN EVO
WHEN HE DIDN'T PRACTICE?
HE MAYBE GOOD BUT
THAT'S JUST FREAKIN' CRAZY.
- I REMEMBER READING SOMETHING
IN A CAR MAGAZINE ONCE,
FOR SHEER SPEEDS ON THE STREETS
THE LAN EVO IS SECOND TO NONE.
SORRY, FD, BUT THIS
IS ONE LESSON
YOUR GONNA HAVE TO LEARN
THE HARD WAY.
TIME FOR TRASH TALK
IS OVER, PRETTY BOY,
NOW GET OUT OF MY SIGHT!
- YOU KNOW I THINK I GET IT NOW.
THE POINT OF THIS RACE IS
ACTUALLY PRETTY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
UNLESS I'M WRONG,
KEISUKE IS FACING TWO MAJOR
HANDICAPS OUT THERE.
ONE, HE'S HAVING TO
DRIVE SOMEONE ELSE'S CAR,
AND TWO, HE NEVER GOT THE CHANCE
TO DO ANY PRACTICE RUNS
ON THIS COURSE.
UNDER CIRCUMSTANCES LIKE THESE,
YOU WOULDN'T THINK HE HAD
A CHANCE TO WIN.
BUT IF THERE'S THE SLIGHTEST
GAP IN HIS OPPONENT'S SKILL,
IT'LL LEVEL THE PLAYING
FIELD FOR HIM.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE SAYING
KEISUKE'S BETTER THAN THIS GUY
WOULD BE THE UNDERSTATEMENT
OF THE YEAR.
- OH YEAH, YOU THINK SO?
- IT'S KINDA HARD TO EXPLAIN.
MY INSTINCTS TELL ME HIS
OPPONENT'S NOT MUCH OF A DRIVER
TO BEGIN WITH.
I THINK IF KEISUKE WAS
GOING TOE-TO-TOE WITH HIM
UNDER NORMAL CONDITIONS, THIS
RACE WOULD BE OVER BY NOW.
- I GET IT.
- IT'S ONLY BECAUSE
OF THOSE HANDICAPS THAT
HE'S BEEN BEHIND THIS DOUCHE
BAG FOR AS LONG AS HE HAS.
THAT'S WHAT THE HILL CLIMB
IS ABOUT. YOU'LL SEE.
- WHY CAN'T I SHAKE THIS GUY?
DAMN IT.
- ( tires screeching )
- C'MON! I'M DRIVING A LAN EVO
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD!
I NEARLY LOST IT BACK
THERE FLOORING IT
THROUGH THE TIGHTEST CORNER
ON THIS TRACK
AND THE BASTARD'S STILL
RIGHT ON TOP OF ME!
HOW CAN SOMEONE BE THAT GOOD
WHEN THEY HAVEN'T RUN
THE COURSE BEFORE?
- GO ANY SLOWER AND THAT
PRISSY LIL' RIDE OF YOURS
MIGHT AS WELL BE
GOIN' BACKWARDS.
- ♪ I NEED A SUPER HOT STUFF ♪
♪ I WANNA TAKE IT ALL TONIGHT ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'M CRAZY ♪
♪ WELL THANK YOU BABY ♪
♪ TURN ON THE POWER,
THE MUSIC LOUDER ♪
♪ COME ON AND TAKE A CHANCE ♪
♪ YOU'LL FEEL ME PUMPIN' REELIN'
TO THE BEAT OF YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ KINGO KING'O BEAT
WE'RE DANCIN' IN THE STREET ♪
♪ A KING OF RULIN' POWER
SO LET'S FREAK OUT TOGETHER ♪
♪ KINGO KING'O BEAT
SO LET YOUR BODY FREE ♪
- THERE'S THE LINE TO TAKE.
RIGHT THERE ON THOSE
UPCOMING S-CURVES.
DON'T SCREW THIS UP. JUST
COME AT HIM FROM THE INSIDE,
TIGHT AS YOU CAN.
IT'LL BE TRICKY, THE EVO
WILL GET JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF DISTANCE ON ME.
BUT IF I DO THIS RIGHT,
THE LINE'LL OPEN OUT
ON THE NEXT LEFT-HANDER AND GIVE
ME SOME CORNERING SPEED.
ONCE WE HIT THE LONG
SRAIGHTAWAY,
I'LL LEAVE HIM IN THE DUST!
THAT'S THE SAME EXIT-ORIENTED
CORNERING STRATEGY I USED
AGAINST THE R34 IN TOCHIGI.
THE LAN EVO DOESN'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST IT.
TIME TO TAKE THIS PUNK
TO SCHOOL!
- YOU IDIOT! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
THE ROAD UP AHEAD IS
UNDER CONSTRUCTION.
THERE'S A BARRICADE
ON THE LEFT SHOULDER!
IT'S NOT WIDE ENOUGH
FOR BOTH CARS!
DON'T GET ANY CLOSER TO ME,
YOU MORON!
YOU'RE GONNA PUSH ME
INTO THE FRIGGIN' EMBANKMENT!
( screaming )
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
- EASY, BIG GUY.
- ( gasping )
- ( tires screeching )
- CRAZY BASTARD!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
WHAT KIND OF HORSE SHIT WERE YOU
TRYING TO PULL BACK THERE?
YOU COULD HAVE KILLED BOTH OF US
WITH THAT LITTLE STUNT OF YOURS!
IS THAT PROJECT D'S IDEA
OF A FAIR RACE?
IF I HADN'T BACKED OFF
AT THE LAST SECOND
WE'D HAVE HAD ONE HELL OF
A MESS ON OUR HANDS.
THANKS TO YOU.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME. YOU DON'T
ACTUALLY BELIEVE THAT, DO YOU?
- WAIT, WHAT?
- YOU MEAN YOU REALLY
HAVE NO CLUE?
- THE HELL YOU SAYIN'?
- THERE WAS JUST
ENOUGH CLEARANCE
THAT IF YOU'D PULLED YOUR CAR
ALL THE WAY OVER TO THE RIGHT,
WE COULDA BOTH GOTTEN THROUGH.
BUT HEY, YOU KNOW THE COURSE
BETTER THAN I DO, RIGHT?
IF YOU COULDN'T JUDGE THAT
FOR YOURSELF,
THERE'S NO POINT IN ME
TRYIN' TO CONVINCE YOU.
I COULD UNDERSTAND
YOU BEING PISSED
IF WE'D HAD CENTRIFUGAL
FORCE PUSHING ON US,
BUT IT WAS A FRIGGIN'
STRAIGHTAWAY.
IF I'D HAVE HAD MY CAR TWO
CENTIMETERS FROM THE BARRICADE,
THERE'D STILL HAVE BEEN FIVE
CENTIMETERS OF PLAY
BETWEEN YOU AND THE GUARDRAIL.
- YOU COULDN'T TELL THAT?
- HUH?
NO WAY IN HELL
ANYONE COULD TELL THAT.
- LOOK IF YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND YOUR OWN CARS,
BET THIS CONVERSATION
IS POINTLESS.
NEXT TIME YOU WANT TO
COME AT ME LIKE THIS,
DO IT ON THE COURSE NOT BY
BITCHING ABOUT MY TECHNIQUE
AFTER THE RACE IS OVER,
YOU KNOW LIKE AN ACTUAL DRIVER.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY A FULL SPEED
BREAKING CONTEST SOMETIME,
THAT'LL SHOW YOU WHAT A REAL
STREET BATTLE IS LIKE.
RIGHT NOW YOU CAN'T EVEN
TALK TO ME.
I THINK THAT'S ABOUT DONE GIVING
FREE LESSONS, HOTSHOT.
NOW WHY DON'T YOU RUN ALONG AND
STOP WASTING EVERYONE'S TIME.
- JUST AS I EXPECTED.
- UH-HUH.
- THANKS A LOT.
YOU'VE GOT ONE HELL OF A CAR.
- ( growling )
- HEY DON'T TRY TO START
ANYTHING WITH HIM, MAN.
NOT WHILE THE GALLERY
IS WATCHING.
- THIS ISN'T GOOD.
I DIDN'T THINK WE COULD LOSE
ON THE HILL CLIMB.
BUT OUR NEXT OPPONENT'S A KID.
I DON'T THINK I'VE GOT THAT MUCH
TO WORRY ABOUT.
( laughing )
- LOOKS TO ME LIKE THEY JUST
REMOVED THE REAR WING
FROM THE LAN EVO, HUH.
MIGHT BE THE EVO SIX? HARD TO
TELL. HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ONE?
- YEAH, A WHILE AGO.
LOOKS LIKE IT.
- YOU AND ME NEED TO
HAVE A LITTLE CHAT
BEFORE WE START, SPORT.
MAN, YOU'RE A YOUNG ONE, HUH?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, KID?
- IT'S FUJIWARA.
- WELL, FUJIWARA.
I'D HATE TO BE THE ONE
TO TELL YOU THIS
BUT JUST BETWEEN YOU AND ME
YOU AND YOUR
LITTLE CREW OVER THERE
ARE IN FOR A WORLD OF HURT.
- WHAT?
- MY BUDDY DIDN'T APPRECIATE
YOUR BOY YELLING AT HIM.
HE MAY HAVE GONE OFF
THE DEEP END .
HE'S PRETTY MUCH THE WORST
KIND OF SORE LOSER,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
HE JUST CALLED A BUNCH
OF HIS BRUISER CRONIES OVER
TO COME AND KICK
YOUR FRIENDS' ASSES.
QUIT GIVING ME
THE STINK EYE, DUDE.
I DON'T WANT THIS COMIN'
TO BLOWS ANY MORE THAN YOU DO.
I JUST THOUGHT A HEADS-UP
MIGHT BE IN ORDER
SEEIN' AS HOW NONE OF THIS
HAS TO GO DOWN,
IF YOU DECIDE TO HELP
SMOOTH OUT THE SITUATION.
SEE WHAT I'M GETTING AT?
MAYBE YOU DON'T TRY SO HARD
TO WIN THIS THING.
- WHAT?
- MAYBE MY SORE LOSER FRIEND
SAVES SOME FACE WATCHIN' ME
PULL OUT THE WIN OVER YOU
AND DECIDES TO CALL
HIS CRONIES OFF, YOU KNOW?
- WHY DON'T YOU
JUST SAY IT, MAN,
EITHER I TAKE A DIVE TONIGHT,
OR MY FRIENDS GET BEATEN UP.
- HEY, DON'T GO PUTTIN' WORDS
IN MY MOUTH, KIDDO.
I'M JUST TRYIN' TO DO THE
NEIGHBORLY THING HERE,
THAT'S ALL.
I'M JUST SAYIN' THERE ARE A LOT
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
THAN WINNING.
LIKE BEIN' ABLE TO WALK.
- ( engine revving )
- WELL, ISN'T THIS FAMILIAR.
ONCE AGAIN THE PRESSURE'S
ON ME TO WIN THIS FOR US
SINCE A CERTAIN SOMEBODY
COULDN'T PULL THEIR OWN WEIGHT.
NOT THAT I'M POINTING
ANY FINGERS.
- ( grunting )
- WHATEVER HAPPENS WE'VE GOTTA
WIN AT LEAST ONE OF THESE.
HOPEFULLY MY LITTLE
HEART-TO-HEART
WILL HAVE DONE THE TRICK.
- EARTH TO TAKUMI.
YOU'RE LOOKIN' A LITTLE
GRIM THERE, EVEN FOR YOU.
YOU SURE
EVERYTHING'S ALRIGHT?
- ACTUALLY THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU PROBABLY OUGHT TO KNOW.
- THOSE SONS-A-BITCHES.
- I DON'T KNOW MAN WHAT
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD DO?
- WHAT DO I THINK
YOU SHOULD DO?
I THINK YOU SHOULD IGNORE THE
BASTARD AND FOCUS ON WINNING.
FORGET ABOUT EVERYTHING BUT THE
ROAD IN FRONT OF YOU
AND LET US HANDLE
EVERYTHING ELSE.
YOU'RE HERE TO RACE,
NOT TO BE INTIMIDATED BY TRASH
TALKING SCUM LIKE HIM.
- I FIGURED YOU'D SAY THAT.
I WAS THINKIN' THE
SAME THING MYSELF.
- ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE.
LET'S DO IT!
STARTING IN FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE.
GO!
- BOTH KEISUKE AND TAKUMI
ARE BEYOND
NEEDING MY ADVICE ANYMORE.
I CAN GIVE THEM FREE RANGE
TO GO WHEREVER
THEIR INSTINCTS LEAD THEM.
STILL, THE EVO SIX IS
NOTHING TO SNEEZE AT.
AS HARMLESS AS IT MAY LOOK,
THAT UNASSUMING LITTLE RAG
CAN BE QUITE THE BOMBSHELL
ON A DOWNHILL RUN.
- I USUALLY WOULDN'T
EXPECT TO DO TO WELL
AGAINST PROJECT D'S
NOTORIOUS EIGHT SIX.
NOT IN AN HONEST RACE ANYWAY.
BUT IF I CAN KEEP THIS KID
FROM GETTING' IN THE ZONE, WELL,
I MEAN, WHO
COULD BLAME A GUY
FOR WANTIN' SOME
INSURANCE, RIGHT?
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF
MY LITTLE SIDEWAYS TAC, REALLY.
NO MATTER HOW GOOD THEY ARE,
ANYONE CAN BE INTIMIDATED
BY VIOLENCE.
HEY, I'M NOT ASKIN'
FOR MUCH HERE,
JUST FOR THE KID TO HAVE
A LITTLE PERSPECTIVE.
JUST HANG BACK AND
TAKE IT EASY SPORT,
THAT'S ALL YOU GOTTA DO, LEAVE
EVERYTHING ELSE TO ME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS THAT
IT WAS WRONG ♪