- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- WELCOME, SIR.
OH, TAKUMI, IT'S YOU.
- HEY, ITSUKI AROUND?
- ACTUALLY, NO.
- YEAH? WHERE IS HE?
- HE, UH, TOOK THE DAY OFF AND
HE MIGHT TAKE TOMORROW OFF, TOO.
- WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
- PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T TALK ABOUT IT.
BUT ITSUKI MIGHT
HAVE GOTTEN HOSED.
HAD SOME PRETTY ROUGH
BUSINESS GO DOWN
WITH THIS GIRL LAST NIGHT.
- WHAT? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THAT SUCKS.
- NOPE. THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
AND FOR HIM TO TAKE
OFF TIME FROM WORK,
IT MUST'VE REALLY STUNG.
- OH, MAN. I NEVER THOUGHT
SHE WOULD'VE DONE THAT TO HIM.
- LOVE TRIANGLES LIKE THAT
HAPPEN ALL THE TIME,
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S ALWAYS
A LOSER. IT JUST BLOWS THIS TIME
'CAUSE ITSUKI THOUGHT
HE WAS GOLDEN WITH HER.
- IN THE END, I THINK
KAZUMI MADE THE CALL
BASED ON WHAT SHE
SAW AS EXPERIENCE.
OR ITSUKI'S LACK OF IT,
TO BE BLUNT.
- I GUESS YOU SHOULD KNOW.
WASN'T IT THE SAME STORY
BETWEEN YOU AND macho?
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BE POINTING ANY FINGERS.
- WELL, NEITHER ARE YOU.
SO SHUT UP.
MY HEART STILL ACHES FROM
THE WHOLE THING.
- HEY, WOULD YOU MIND
GIVING ITSUKI A RING LATER
AND SEEING IF HE'S
FEELING ANY BETTER?
- YEAH, I'LL MAKE SURE
TO DO THAT.
BUT I SUCK AT THAT KINDA THING.
I NEVER KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
- IT'D PROBABLY BE BEST IF YOU
GUYS LEFT THE POOR FOOL ALONE.
NOW, LISTEN, IF ITSUKI DOES
SHOW FOR WORK TOMORROW,
I DON'T WANT ANY OF YOU
EVEN MENTIONING THIS BUSINESS
ABOUT HIM GETTING DUMPED.
ARE WE CLEAR ON THAT?
- CRYSTAL.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY, BOSS.
- ( car approaching )
- GO AHEAD AND FILL HER UP WITH
HIGH OCTANE, AND MAKE IT FAST.
- Iketani: YES, SIR. NO PROBLEM.
COMING RIGHT UP.
- HEY, MAN. ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
- HOLD THAT THOUGHT, TAKUMI,
I'M GLAD I FOUND YOU.
THERE'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
- YOU CAME HERE TO TALK TO ME?
- LOOK FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
I FEEL BAD ABOUT WHAT WENT
DOWN WITH ITSUKI.
WOULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND TELL HIM SOMETHING FOR ME?
TELL HIM I SAID HE NEEDS
TO FORGET
ALL ABOUT MY LITTLE SISTER
AND FIND HIMSELF A NICE GIRL.
ONE THAT WILL TREAT HIM RIGHT.
- SO, THIS IS WHAT A
SUPERCHARGER FEELS LIKE
FROM THE INSIDE.
MAN, IT'S A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
FEEL FROM MY EIGHT-SIX.
- I CLOCKED IN OVER
TWO HUNDRED HORSEPOWER
LAST TIME I PUT IT
ON THE CHASSIS DYNAMO.
BUT WHEN I TAKE HER OUT
ON A HIGH-SPEED UPHILL
LIKE MT. AKINA,
YOU CAN'T TELL THERE'S A
SUPERCHARGER UNDER THE HOOD.
IT TAKES TIGHT PASSES
LIKE THE ONES IN CHICHIBU
FOR YOU TO REALLY SEE WHAT
KIND OF A BOOST IT GETS.
- WELL, YOU'VE BEATEN
THE NORTHERN SAITAMA ALLIANCE.
AND NOW THAT YOU'VE
STOMPED US INTO THE GROUND,
YOUR RUNNING OUT OF CHALLENGES
HERE IN SAITAMA.
BUT IF YOU REALLY WANT TO DOT
THE I'S ON YOUR TRIP HERE,
THERE'S ON MORE GROUP YOU MIGHT
WANNA PUT YOUR SIGHTS ON.
I'M WARNING YOU, THEY'RE
A SHADY BUNCH OF PRICKS.
BUT JUST TALKING
ABOUT THEIR SKILL LEVEL,
THEY SHOULDN'T GIVE YOU
A WHOLE LOT OF TROUBLE.
- SO...
- HUH?
- LOOK, THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT I'VE BEEN WANTING
TO ASK YOU FOR A WHILE NOW.
I WAS CURIOUS IF YOU EVER
FELT LIKE YOU WERE KINDA BEING
HELD BACK BY THE EIGHT-SIX'S
LIMITED CAPABILITIES.
- HUH? WELL, YEAH, DUDE,
OF COURSE I DO.
I MEAN, WHY WOULDN'T I?
WHY ELSE DO YOU THINK
I JACK IT UP WITH THINGS
LIKE THE SUPERCHARGER
AND THE TURBO?
I MESS WITH IT
ALL THE TIME, MAN.
EVEN IN THE RAIN
THE OTHER NIGHT,
I CAUGHT MYSELF WISHING
THAT THE LEVIN'S BODY
WAS A LITTLE LIGHTER,
MORE UPDATED. STARTED
TO WEAR ON ME AFTER A WHILE.
TO BE HONEST I'M SURPRISED
TO HEAR THAT YOU'VE HAD
THE SAME CONCERNS ABOUT
IT, YOU KNOW.
I GUESS I SORT OF
THOUGHT THAT YOU WERE
ABOVE IT OR SOMETHING,
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN YOU'VE GONE UP AGAINST
ALL KINDS OF DIFFERENT CARS
IN THE EIGHT-SIX,
AND YOU HAVEN'T LOST YET.
- OKAY, I HAVEN'T
TOLD ANYONE THIS,
BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED
THE OTHER NIGHT.
- I SORT OF GOT PASSED
ON MY HOME COURSE.
- HUH?
- ( sighs )
I HAVE A HARD TIME
BELIEVING THAT.
YOU KNOW THE PASS LIKE THE BACK
OF YOUR HAND. I'VE SEEN YOU.
- WHAT KINDA CAR WAS IT?
- A SUBARU IMPREZA.
- MAKES SENSE,
THAT'S A FOUR WHEEL DRIVE.
- I'VE BEEN FEELING REALLY WEIRD
ABOUT IT EVER SINCE IT HAPPENED.
IT'S LIKE I'VE WORKED MYSELF UP
INTO SOME KIND OF FOUR-WHEEL
DRIVE ANXIETY COMPLEX.
- MAYBE SO.
BUT REMEMBER YOU'VE GONE
UP AGAINST A LAN EVO
BEFORE AND YOU'VE WON.
DON'T FOCUS SO MUCH ATTENTION
ON THE FACT THAT IT'S
A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE
IT'LL ONLY SCREW YOU UP.
- I KNOW AND I'M TRYING NOT TO
BUT IT DOESN'T SEEM TO HELP.
- ( tires screeching )
- I KNOW IT SHOULDN'T HAVE
SHAKEN ME UP SO BAD, BUT IT DID.
SO, IF THERE IS ANY ADVICE
YOU COULD GIVE ME,
I WOULD REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
- DAMN, DUDE I DON'T KNOW.
- I'VE HAD TO DEAL WITH
THE LIMIT'S OF THE EIGHT-SIX
MORE TIMES THAN
I'D LIKE TO ADMIT.
BUT WHEN YOU REALLY BREAK
IT DOWN, IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF YOU'RE GOING UP
AGAINST A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE,
AN FF, AN FR, OR WHAT.
ALL NEW CARS ARE SCARY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
ALL OF THEM?
- NOTHING WRONG WITH A LITTLE
BIT OF FEAR AS LONG AS YOU USE
IT TO YOUR ADVANTAGE.
I WORKED MY ASS OFF TO IMPROVE
ON MY OWN SKILLS,
TRYING TO MAKE UP FOR
THE WEAKNESSES OF THE CAR.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK I KNOW
SOMETHING THAT MIGHT BE USEFUL.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'LL HELP YOU
WITH YOUR COMPLEX
BUT IT SURE AS HELL
HELPED ME GET OVER MINE.
YOU DON'T KNOW IT YET,
BUT YOUR NEXT OPPONENT WILL
PROBABLY BE A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
UP UNTIL LAST YEAR, YOU WERE
ABLE TO KEEP KNOCKING OUT WINS
WITH NO KNOWLEDGE OR INFORMATION
OR ANY BACKGROUND IN THIS STUFF.
BUT NO MATTER HOW GOOD
A DRIVER YOU ARE,
AT SOME POINT YOUR GOING
TO HIT A WALL.
BEFORE NOW YOU'VE BEATEN
FOUR-WHEEL DRIVES
BY GOING AS HARD
AS YOU KNOW HOW,
NOT BY UNDERSTANDING
YOUR OPPONENTS.
THAT'S THE DEFINITION
OF A CLUELESS VICTORY.
BUT I THINK YOU'RE STILL
ATTACKING THE PROBLEMS
OF THE EIGHT-SIX
IN THE RIGHT WAY.
SO, JUST DEAL
WITH THE FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE
LIKE YOU TACKLE ANY OTHER
CAR YOU'RE FACING.
KNOW THEIR ADVANTAGES
AND EXPLOIT THE HELL OUT
OF THEIR WEAKNESSES.
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP
WINNING, GET CREATIVE.
YOUR UPCOMING BATTLE
WILL BE THE PERFECT CHANCE.
TRY TO PUT SOME SERIOUS
BRAIN POWER ON IT
AND FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO DEFEAT THE FOUR-WHEEL DRIVES.
- TELL ME SOMETHING
I DON'T KNOW?
BUT HOW AM I GOING TO DO THAT?
- 'COURSE IT GETS PRETTY BORING
IF YOU ALWAYS KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT, SO
DON'T GO OVERBOARD.
YOUR NATURAL CLUELESSNESS
IS WHAT MAKES YOU A UNIQUE
PACKAGE, TAKUMI.
- STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES
OF A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE, HUH?
WATARU WAS RIGHT.
LAST YEAR I WAS DRIVING MY
HARDEST WITHOUT KNOWING
A THING. ON A SCALE
OF ONE TO TEN,
MY IGNORANCE WAS AT
A NINE POINT FIVE.
'COURSE NOW I KNOW
MORE ABOUT FOUR-WHEEL DRIVES
THAN I EVER WANTED TO.
I'M NOT SURE THOUGH. I
DON'T THINK THIS IS
AS SIMPLE AS HE MAKING IT SOUND.
MAN, IF THIS THING HAS
A WEAKNESS,
I HAVE NO CLUE WHAT IT IS?
- Kuro: WHAT DO YOU
WANNA TALK ABOUT?
- Shiro: OKAY,
KEEP THIS BETWEEN US,
BUT IF WE WIN THIS NEXT BATTLE
WE GOT COMING UP,
I THINK WE CAN
MAKE SOME CASH OFF IT.
- HUH?
- LOOK, PROJECT D
IS PRETTY FAMOUS, RIGHT?
SO SAY OUR EVO'S WIN THIS RACE
WE GOT WITH THEM.
THAT WOULD SO BOOST SALES FOR
THE SHOP THAT HELPS US OUT.
AND IF THEY POST THIS WIN
ALL OVER THE NET,
YOU KNOW THEY'LL START
GETTING HIT'S FROM ALL OVER.
SERIOUSLY, TELL ME THAT WOULDN'T
BRING IN THE CUSTOMERS
FOR THOSE GREASE MONKEYS.
- I SEE WHAT YOU'RE GETTING AT.
SO, HOW MUCH DO YOU
THINK WE CAN GET?
- WIN BOTH RACES,
FIVE HUNDRED THOU.
ONE RACE, TWO HUNDRED
AND FIFTY THOU.
WE TIE, I WORKED IT OUT SO
THAT WE STILL GET FIFTY GRAND.
- COOL, YOU GOT TO BE
SHITTING ME.
- NOPE.
- A WIN AGAINST THESE GUYS
WON'T BE SO EASY.
- BUT I GOT NO INTENTIONS
OF RUNNING A FAIR RACE
TO BEGIN WITH.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF WE CHEAT.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS GET
'EM THE RESULTS,
THEY GET US THE CASH
AND WE'RE HOME FREE.
AND IF I KNOW ANYBODY
THAT CAN CHEAT LIKE A PRO,
KURO, MY MAN, IT'S YOU.
- ( chuckles )
I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE
MUCH ROOM TO TALK, SHIRO.
- THERE THEY GO.
- WATARU SAID WE'D BE UP
AGAINST FOUR-WHEEL DRIVES NEXT.
AND SURE ENOUGH
THESE GUYS DRIVE LAN EVOS.
- Kuro: NO WAY?
- HEY, RYOSUKE, WE NEED
TO SEE YOU OVER HERE.
THESE GUYS HAVE
A REQUEST TO MAKE.
THEY'RE SAYING
THEY WANNA SPLIT UP
THE PRACTICE TIME
BETWEEN OUR TEAMS.
I FIGURED YOU MIGHT
WANT TO WEIGH IN.
IT'S NOT HOW WE'VE
DONE IT BEFORE.
COULD THROW US OFF OUR GAME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
WE HAVE TO SPLIT THE TIME.
CAN'T WE JUST PRACTICE TOGETHER?
- I DON'T THINK WE'D FEEL
VERY COMFORTABLE DOING THAT.
YOU SEE THE THING IS,
WE DON'T LIKE PRACTICING
WITH PEOPLE WHOSE SKILLS WE'RE
NOT TOO SURE OF, YOU UNDERSTAND.
I GOT NO IDEA
HOW YOU GUYS DRIVE.
LOOK, I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOU TAKE A CORNER TOO WIDE
AND WIPE ME OUT
DURING A PRACTICE RUN.
- YOU GOT TRUST ISSUES, PAL,
OR ARE YOU TRYING TO BE A DICK?
- JUST STAY OUT OF THIS, YOU'RE
ONLY GOING TO MAKE THINGS WORSE?
- THIS IS SCREWED UP.
- DON'T GET BENT OUT OF SHAPE.
ALL I'M SAYING IS THIS,
WE SPLIT OUR PRACTICE TIME
EVENLY UNTIL THE SUN COMES UP.
C'MON, GUYS,
WHAT'S WITH THE ATTITUDE?
I MEAN IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
WE CAN JUST FORGET
THIS WHOLE THING.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE GOT ANY REASON
TO GO OUT OF OUR WAY
TO RACE YOU, GUYS.
WE GOT NOTHING TO PROVE.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANT TO DO THIS?
- BRO, WAIT.
- NO. THE DECISION IS MADE.
- WHY ARE WE TRYING TO
PRETEND THAT THIS IS FAIR?
IT'S A BAD FREAKING JOKE.
I MEAN, GIVE ME A BREAK.
THEY'RE THE DAMN LOCALS.
THEY DRIVE THIS
COURSE EVERY DAY.
ALL THIS COMES DOWN TO IS
THEM NOT WANTING US
TO GET ENOUGH
PRACTICE TIME IN.
- I NEVER DEALT WITH
JERKS LIKE THIS BEFORE.
MAN, THEY PISS ME OFF.
- UP UNTIL TONIGHT, WE'VE ONLY
GONE UP AGAINST GUYS
WHO MAY HAVE HAD A PLAN
UP THEIR SLEEVE,
BUT DAMN IT, IF THAT PLAN WASN'T
AT LEAST CLEAN AND FAIR.
THESE IDIOTS THINK
THAT THEY CAN TRIP US UP
BY CUTTING OUR PRACTICE
TIME IN HALF.
BUT IT'LL JUST MAKE IT
JUST THAT MUCH MORE
EMBARRASSING WHEN THEY LOSE.
TOMORROW, THEY'RE GONNA SEE
EXACTLY THE KIND OF IDIOTS
PROJECT D CAN MAKE 'EM.
- YOU KNOW I WAS THINKING
THIS MIGHT BE THE EXACTLY
THE KIND OF CHALLENGE
TAKUMI NEEDS
TO REALLY MOVE HIM UP TO
THE NEXT LEVEL AS A DRIVER.
HE'LL HAVE TO SET UP HIS CAR
AND MASTER THIS COURSE
IN ABOUT HALF THE TIME
HE USUALLY HAS TO DO
THE SAME AMOUNT OF WORK,
THAT'S A MAJOR SWITCH.
- YEAH, I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THESE GUYS,
THAT THEY MAY BE TRYING
TO PULL SOME KIND OF SCAM.
- YEAH, WHAT KIND?
- I'M NOT SURE.
BUT UNTIL I AM, I WANT
YOU TO KEEP YOUR GUARD UP.
- YOU WON'T HAVE MUCH TIME,
SO SCORCH THE WHOLE COURSE
AND THE ROAD CONDITIONS
INTO YOUR MIND. GOT IT?
- IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME. WE CAN
FINALLY GET OUT THERE
AND START LEARNING THIS ROAD.
HEY, REALLY TRY TO GET SOME
WORK IN BEFORE THE SUN COMES UP.
NO SLAKING OUT THERE.
- STANDING BY, I'M READY
WHENEVER YOU ARE KEISUKE.
- OKAY.
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ GIVE ME LOVE ♪
♪ GIVE ME LOVE ♪
- WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME.
WE NEED TO BE AS
EFFICIENT AS WE CAN.
- THEN, LET'S GET THIS
SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- YOUR PUNK ASSES WON'T BE ABLE
TO STAY SO COCKY
FOR MUCH LONGER.
I THINK OUR BEST SHOT
AT PULLING OUT THIS WIN
IS TO PUT OUR SIGHTS
ON THE FD INSTEAD
OF THE EIGHT-SIX.
- OH, I GET IT. YOU WANT
THE EASY WIN FOR YOURSELF, HUH?
- SHUT UP, MAN, THAT'S NOT IT.
I JUST THINK THAT THE FREAK
DRIVING THE FD NEEDS
A GOOD PUBLIC BITCH SLAP.
GUY HAD THE NERVE TO STARE
ME DOWN LIKE A CHUMP.
I'M GONNA MAKE THAT PUNK CRY
IN FRONT OF ALL HIS
LITTLE FREAK FRIENDS.
- YEAH, COOL,
WHATEVER YOU SAY, MAN.
RUN YOU RACE HOWEVER YOU WANT,
I STILL GET HALF THE CASH?
- ( cellphone dialing )
- HEY, IT'S ME. I NEED YOU
TO LISTEN UP, I'VE GOT INFO.
OUR TARGET'S GONNA BE THE FD.
- HEY. SO, ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS MAN?
THEY'LL KILL US IF
THEY CATCH US.
- YOU LET ME WORRY ABOUT THAT.
- OKAY. BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M GOING TO BE ABLE
TO HIT THE TIMING JUST RIGHT.
I MAKE ONE MISTAKE AND I WILL
END UP HITTING THEM BOTH
AND NONE OF US WANTS TO SEE
WHAT THAT WRECK WILL LOOK LIKE.
- HEY, IF IT HAPPENS,
IT HAPPENS.
( laughs )
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
HE SAYS WE TARGET THE FD.
- ( No Control playing )
- ♪ GIVE ME MAGIC ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ GIVE ME POWER ♪
♪ GIVE ME PLAY ♪
♪ GIVE ME MAGIC ♪
♪ GIVE ME HIGH ♪
♪ GIVE ME PLAY ♪
- ONLY HAVING HALF THE TIME
TO RUN THE COURSE SUCKS BAD.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE THE TIME
TO THINK ABOUT
BEATING THE
FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE.
ALL I CAN REALLY FOCUS ON
IS BEATING THE COURSE.
I'M GETTING BOUNCED
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
AND I GOTTA HAVE EVER POINT
WHERE THE CAR JUMPS MEMORIZED.
- IT MAY BE THE SMOOTHEST
SURFACE I'VE EVER DRIVEN ON,
BUT OTHER THAN THAT,
IT'S AN EASY COURSE.
- ♪ NO CONTROL NOT AT ALL ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU MAKE ME
FEEL CRAZY NOW ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONNA BREAK ME DOWN ♪
♪ OH, BABY, NO CONTROL
IN MY SOUL, EVEN IN MY MIND ♪
♪ BUT IF YOU CALL I'LL BE FINE ♪
♪ NO CONTROL ♪
- I LOVE THE PRACTICE RUNS.
EVERY TIME I PASS HIM,
I GET TO REMIND MYSELF THAT
I'M NEVER GONNA LOSE TO HIM.
MY FD IS FEELING
SOLID TONIGHT.
IF EVERYTHING KEEPS
UP LIKE THIS,
WE'LL HAVE THIS THING
WRAPPED UP EARLY.
I'LL RUN A PERFECT COURSE.
WHAT'S THAT ON THE ROAD.
IS THAT WATER?
IT WASN'T THERE WHEN
I PASSED EARLIER.
THAT'S NOT WATER. THAT'S OIL.
( Keisuke panting )
- DUDE, ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( on phone) YEAH, FUMIHIRO.
THIS IS KEISUKE.
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
YOU SOUND WEIRD.
- HELL, YEAH.
THOSE GUYS STILL THERE?
- WHAT, YOU MEAN THE GUYS THAT
WE'RE GOING UP AGAINST TOMORROW?
NO, NOT ANYMORE. THEY BLEW
OUT OF HERE A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
WHY? IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- YES, LISTEN,
IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
STOP THE EIGHT-SIX RIGHT NOW.
DON'T LET HIM COME BACK
MY WAY. YOU GOT ME?
- DUDE, SLOW DOWN WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT? WHAT HAPPENED?
- SOMEBODY DUMPED A FEW
GALLONS OF OIL ACROSS THE ROAD.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME? WHERE ARE
YOU NOW? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HOW'S YOUR CAR?
IS MIYAGUCHI STILL WITH YOU?
- I'M OKAY BUT I GOT
SOME BAD NEWS, GUYS.
MY FD... SHE'S ALL BUSTED UP.
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU COULD
HAVE AVOIDED THIS, KEISUKE,
NOBODY COULD.
- DAMN, THIS SUCKS,
WHO WOULD'VE DONE THIS?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS, MAN?
WHO ELSE WOULD WANT TO
SCREW UP MY RIDE?
- WHOEVER DID THIS
HAD AN ESCAPE ROUTE.
THEY MUST HAVE LEFT DOWN
THAT ROAD IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
ON THE MAP, IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S WIDE ENOUGH FOR ONE CAR.
GOES ALL THE WAY
TO THE NEXT TOWN.
- IF SO, THEN WHY
DON'T WE GET A MOVE ON
AND TRY TO BEAT THEM
TO THE EXIT ON THE OTHER END?
WE SHOULD HAVE ENOUGH TIME
TO CATCH THEIR PUNK ASSES
WHEN THEY COME
SLITHERING OUT.
THAT'S WHERE I'M GOING.
I'M TAKING UNIT ONE.
- HEY, HOLD UP, KEISUKE.
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
- CUT IT OUT, YOU TWO.
THERE'S NO POINT IN YOU
CHASING THEM DOWN.
- YEAH, THERE IS.
NOBODY DOES THAT TO MY BABY
AND GETS AWAY WITH IT.
MESS WITH ANOTHER DUDE'S CAR
AND YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR IT.
THEY SHOULD KNOW THAT
AND IF THEY DON'T,
I'M GONNA HUNT THEM DOWN
AND TEACH IT TO THEM.
- DON'T MAKE ME REPEAT
MYSELF, KEISUKE,
I TOLD YOU TO CALM DOWN.
- Fumihiro: HOW BAD IS IT?
- Miyaguchi: IT'S PRETTY BAD.
LOOKS LIKE THE SUSPENSION ARM
IS ALL KINDS OF JACKED UP.
AND WITH THIS HARD
OF AN IMPACT,
THE ALIGNMENT PROBABLY
NEEDS TO BE COMPLETELY RESET.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO WAY
WE CAN HAVE THIS SUCKER READY
BY TOMORROW NIGHT.
- BUT THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH THE DRIVETRAIN, IS THERE?
JUST FIX IT UP TO WHERE
I CAN DRIVE AGAIN.
JERRY-RIGGING IF YOU
HAVE TO, ALL RIGHT?
I DON'T EVEN CARE IF SHE WON'T
DRIVE STRAIGHT.
LET ME DEAL WITH THE REST
OF IT ON THE COURSE.
- ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING
TO YOURSELF, KEISUKE.
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT THAT YOU
AREN'T THE MOST CAUTIOUS DRIVER
IN THE WORLD
AND WITH THE SUSPENSION
IN THE SHAPE THAT IT'S IN,
YOUR GOING TO KILL YOURSELF.
- FUMIHIRO IS RIGHT.
YOU REALLY CAN'T PREDICT HOW
THE CAR IS GONNA ACT
WHEN IT'S LIKE THIS.
AND YOUR LIMIT'S OUT THERE ARE
GOING TO BE EXTREMELY LOW.
SORRY, MAN.
YOU'RE JUST NOT GONNA BE
WORTH MUCH IN A BATTLE.
- ( engine revs )
- HERE YOU GUYS ARE.
AND I WONDERED WHY IT'S SO
QUIET UP ON THE MOUNTAIN.
CAN'T BELIEVE, YOU ACTUALLY
WRECKED INTO THIS CORNER.
- THAT WAS DIRTY LITTLE TRICK
YOUR BOYS PULLED
OUT HERE TONIGHT.
AND DON'T PRETEND
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHO SPILLED THE OIL
ACROSS THE ROAD.
- I AIN'T PRETENDING NOTHING.
ALL MY GUYS ARE GEARING
UP FOR THE RACE.
AND I'D APPRECIATE IT IF
YOU WOULDN'T ACCUSE ME
OF B.S. LIKE THAT.
OKAY? BESIDES WHAT PROOF
DO YOU HAVE WE HAD
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH ANYTHING?
- DON'T MESS WITH ME, MAN.
I DON'T NEED ANY PROOF TO
KNOW WHO SABOTAGED MY CAR.
NOW GET OUT HERE AND
WE'LL SETTLE THIS LIKE MEN.
- KEISUKE. KNOCK IT OFF,
OKAY, NOT NOW.
- OH, YOU'RE REALLY SCARY
WHEN YOU GET MAD.
LOOKS LIKE PROJECT D'S
GOT THEMSELVES
A LITTLE BIT OF A LOOSE
CANNON ON THEIR HANDS.
WONDER IF YOU'RE ALL LIKE THAT.
ACCUSE ME OF SOMETHING
WITH NO PROOF,
THEN YOU TRY TO GET ME
TO GET OUT OF MY CAR.
YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN
TAKE ME IN A FIGHT, BIG MAN?
I'M NOT SO SURE
YOU DON'T WANT THAT.
AND I'M NOT SURE I WANT TO RACE
AGAINST ASSHOLES LIKE YOU.
- WE'RE SORRY ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
LET'S FORGET IT EVER HAPPENED.
BUT AS YOU CAN SEE THE FD
WE RACE ON THE UPHILLS
IS IN PRETTY BAD SHAPE.
WE CAN GET IT FIXED UP,
IT'S JUST GOING TO TAKE US
A LITTLE MORE THAN A DAY
TO DO IT RIGHT.
- OH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
AN UNFORTUNATE TURN OF EVENTS.
- I KNOW THIS MIGHT COME OFF
AS A SOMEWHAT SELFISH REQUEST,
BUT DO YOU THINK YOU
COULD POSTPONE THE BATTLE
FOR ANOTHER WEEK?
- GEE, ANOTHER WEEK, HUH?
- YEAH, JUST GIVE US A WEEK
AND WE CAN HAVE HER FIXED,
NO PROBLEM.
- THAT MAKES PERFECT SENSE
AND I UNDERSTAND THE PREDICAMENT
THAT YOU'RE IN. BUT I THINK
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SAY NO.
WE'VE GOT LIVES OUTSIDE
OF RACING, YOU KNOW.
I GOT A DATE NEXT WEEK
AND I AIN'T GONNA CANCELING
'CAUSE YOU SCREWED UP A CAR.
- SON OF A BITCH.
- IN THE RACING WORLD,
THE CAR THAT CAN'T MAKE IT TO
THE STARTING LINE ON TIME
IS THE LOSER BY DEFAULT.
BIG TIME BOYS LIKE YOU
SHOULD KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
SO, KEEP YOUR EXCUSES
TO YOURSELF.
WE'RE DOING THIS THING
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT.
WE START AT EIGHT, I DON'T
CARE IF IT'S THE EIGHT-SIX,
OR A BOX WITH WHEELS
TAPED TO THE BOTTOM,
JUST GET A REPLACEMENT.
AND TRY TO BE ON TIME, HUH?
ONE MINUTE LATE AND YOU
FORFEIT THE RACE,
AND LEAVE SAITAMA WITH
A LOSS UNDER YOUR BELT.
- DAMN IT!
I'M GONNA END THAT PRICK
WHEN I GET THE CHANCE.
- IF YOUR FINISHED
YELLING AT THE GUARDRAIL,
WE'VE GOT WORK TO DO.
FUJIWARA, MATSUMOTO,
YOU TWO FINISH GETTING THE
EIGHT-SIX READY.
- YOU GOT IT.
- WE'LL GET ON IT RIGHT NOW.
- NOT SO FAST, UNTIL WE GET THE
REST OF THAT OIL CLEARED OFF,
SPLIT THE COURSE IN HALF
FOR YOUR PRACTICE.
AND WE'LL GET STARTED
ON CLEAN UP RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE VERY LITTLE
TIME FOR IT, SO LET'S MOVE.
- HOLD ON A SECOND.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
SIT ON MY ASS AND WAIT?
WHAT ABOUT FIXING MY FD?
I'M GONNA NEED A LITTLE HELP.
- IT'D BE POINTLESS TO TRY.
I'VE CONSIDERED EVERY OPTION
AND DECIDED FIXING YOUR CAR
WOULD BE AN EXERCISE
IN FUTILITY AT THIS POINT,
WE JUST DON'T HAVE ENOUGH TIME.
YOU DON'T HAVE A JOB TO DO
ON THIS RACE ANYMORE,
SO, YOU SHOULD START WORKING
FROM THE SIDELINES.
- YOU GOTTA LET ME RACE.
LEAVE ME OUTTA THIS
AND YOU'LL JUST BE GIVING THEM
EXACTLY WHAT THEY WANT.
- YOU REALLY STILL DON'T
UNDERSTAND, DO YOU?
THE REASON THE FD TOOK THE HIT
IT DID WAS BECAUSE OF YOU.
- BECAUSE OF ME?
- THAT'S RIGHT. DO YOU THINK
IF IT'D BEEN ME BEHIND THE WHEEL
THAT I WOULD HAVE FALLEN FOR A
PATHETIC LITTLE TRAP LIKE THAT?
YOUR PRIDE AND CARELESSNESS
GOT THE BEST OF YOU.
NOW, GO COOL AND THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOU DID.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET TO WORK.
- I DON'T BUY THAT. I GET WHAT
HE WAS SAYING,
BUT I THINK HE WAS
TOO HARSH ON YOU.
NO WAY HE COULD HAVE DODGED
THAT MUCH OIL,
I DON'T CARE HOW GOOD
A DRIVER HE IS.
IT WAS EVERYWHERE. I JUST
DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
TAKE WHAT HE
SAID SO SERIOUSLY.
- YOU'RE WRONG. MY BROTHER
COULD'VE DONE IT.
COULD'VE BLOWN OVER THAT SLICK
LIKE IT WAS NOTHING
BUT DRY PAVEMENT AND
KEPT ON ROLLING.
RYOSUKE WAS RIGHT ABOUT
EVERYTHING HE WAS SAYING
AND DEEP DOWN INSIDE,
I KNOW IT'S TRUE.
I'M PISSED OFF AT MYSELF
THAT I FELL RIGHT INTO SUCH
A BUSH LEAGUE TRICK
SO FREAKING EASILY
JUST BECAUSE OF MY ATTITUDE.
IT'S ALL CAUSE OF ME. THAT'S
WHY I GOTTA DRIVE TONIGHT
NO MATTER WHAT.
WHAT THE HELL ELSE
AM I GONNA DO?
TELL ME, KENTA,
WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?
- I JUST... I DON'T KNOW.
- SUCKS TO BE KEISUKE RIGHT NOW,
WANTING TO DRIVE SO BADLY
BUT NOT BEING ABLE TO.
PISSES ME OFF, TOO.
BUT RIGHT NOW, ALL I CAN DO
IS FOCUS ON THE TASK AT HAND.
KEEP MY MIND ON THE RACE AND
BEAT THOSE GUYS INTO THE GROUND.
- ( signing in Japanese )
♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪