- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- RISE AND SHINE.
TIME TO GET MOVING.
- YEAH, I'M UP.
- YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- ( engine running )
- WHAT IS THAT?
IS THAT OUTSIDE?
HOLY CRAP.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- WIPE THAT DUMB EXPRESSION
OFF YOUR FACE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE MAKING
THE DELIVERIES IN THIS TODAY.
I WANT YOU SWITCHING
BETWEEN THIS
AND THE EIGHT-SIX FOR
A LITTLE WHILE.
HEY, YOU GOT THAT?
- IT'S THE SAME CAR. THE SAME
COLOR EVEN THE REAR WING...
- ( tires screeching )
- THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED
THAT NIGHT.
OH, OF COURSE IT ALL MAKES
TOTAL SENSE NOW,
I'M SO BLIND WHY DIDN'T
I PUT IT TOGETHER SOONER?
DAMN IT, I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON ALIVE
WHO DRIVES SO DANGEROUSLY,
SO RECKLESSLY, SO STUPID FAST
ON AKINA'S DOWNHILL.
THAT WAS YOU OUT THERE,
WASN'T IT, DAD?
- IT'S A DAMN SHAME,
BUT THE KID'S GONNA DROP INTO A
SLUMP FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
STILL, HE'S GOT NO FUTURE
IF HE CAN'T GET PAST
DRIVING THE EIGHT-SIX.
IF YOU DON'T SPREAD YOUR
WINGS, YOU HIT THE GROUND.
- THIS IS WILD.
DAMN THAT OLD GEEZER.
HOW COULD HE SAY THAT THIS CAR
IS PRACTICAL AND EASY TO DRIVE?
MUST BE DOING THIS TO MESS
WITH ME OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO
DO WITH THIS THING.
- YOU SAID IT WAS A CAPPUCCINO?
YELLOW LICENSE PLATE
AND EVERYTHING?
- YEAH. SURPRISED US TOO, BOSS.
- BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
THEIR OPPONENTS SURE DO COME UP
WITH SOME INTERESTING TACTICS
WHEN THEY HAVE TO. IT IS
ACTUALLY A PRETTY GOOD IDEA.
I MEAN THOSE K VEHICLES
ARE SOME FAST CARS
WHEN IT COMES TO DOWNHILLS.
I WOULDN'T LIE ABOUT THAT.
- NOT LIKE IT MATTERED.
TAKUMI STILL WON THE NIGHT,
ONE SWEET VICTORY.
YOU KNOW, I WONDER IF THERE'S
A DRIVER OUT THERE
WHO COULD EVER BEAT HIM.
- KEEP AN OPEN MIND. THERE'S
AN ENTIRE WORLD OUT THERE.
NO MATTER HOW GOOD YOU GET,
THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE WHO CAN
KNOCK YOU OFF YOUR THRONE.
- YEAH, BUT, BOSS,
TAKUMI'S DRIVING IS BETTER
THAN YOU'D THINK.
GETTING TO WHERE IT'S
ALMOST UNREAL. RIGHT?
- YOU'RE NOT LYING ABOUT THAT.
TAKUMI'S SKILL BEHIND THE WHEEL
HAS GONE THROUGH THE ROOF
SINCE HE'S JOINED THE D.
STILL I MISS THE OLD TAKUMI.
ALWAYS SPITTING OUT THE MOST
RIDICULOUS NONSENSE ABOUT CARS.
- GOTTA SAY, LAST NIGHT
IT WAS A LONELY FEELING
WATCHING HIM CHAT IT UP
WITH RYOSUKE FROM A DISTANCE.
NOT THAT I WAS JEALOUS
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST THAT I FELT MORE
LIKE A FAN THAN A FRIEND.
THE GUY'S JUST GOTTEN
TO BE SO DISTANT FROM US.
- HUH, I THINK THAT'S JUST ALL
IN YOUR FOGGY TEENAGE BRAINS.
I'VE SEEN TAKUMI AROUND YOU GUYS
AND HE SEEMS THE SAME TO ME.
- ( car approaching )
- WELL, SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
- Kenji: AND THE
DEVIL APPEARS, HUH?
SEE EVEN HIS TIMING HAS
GOTTEN BETTER.
- ON YOUR WAY BACK FROM WORK?
- ITSUKI HAD THE
EARLY SHIFT TODAY,
SO HE'S ALL READY GONE HOME.
- NO, I'M NOT HERE TO SEE HIM.
I JUST HAD A QUICK
QUESTION FOR YOU.
DID MY DAD HAPPEN TO
SAY ANYTHING TO YOU
ABOUT HIM BUYING A NEW CAR?
- YEAH, SURE.
IT'S THAT NEW IMPREZA.
- OH, GREAT.
SO, YOU KNEW ALL ABOUT IT.
- DUDE.
- AN IMPREZA, HUH?
- YOU KNOW WHAT,
THAT OLD MAN CAN REALLY PISS
ME OFF SOMETIMES.
HE'LL TELL ALL HIS BUDDIES
BUT I'VE GOT TO BE
THE LAST ONE TO KNOW.
- WELL, YOU GIVE
THE NEW WHEELS A SPIN?
- YEA, FIRST THING THIS MORNING.
- AND WHAT'D YOU THINK?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I THINK ABOUT IT YET.
IT ALMOST MORE LIKE
BEING BEHIND A WHEEL
OF A FLYING SAUCER THAN A CAR.
- DUDE, YOU SOUND CRAZY AS HELL.
- YEAH, I DON'T GET
WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS, MAN.
- DRIVING IT HAS JUST BEEN
TOO JARRING FOR ME TO HANDLE.
I MEAN, YEAH, I DID IT 'CAUSE
MY DAD WANTED ME TO, BUT NOW...
NOW, I'M ALL CONFUSED.
I HONESTLY DON'T EVEN
THINK I EVEN KNOW
HOW TO DRIVE
THE EIGHT-SIX ANYMORE.
- ( all gasping )
- SORRY, BRO, YOU'RE NOT
MAKING ANY SENSE AT ALL.
I MEAN IF I'D EVER SEEN
YOU LOSE IN THAT CAR,
I MIGHT SEE WHAT YOU'RE GETTING
AT, BUT RIGHT NOW...
- DAMN RIGHT.
- OKAY, MAYBE I'M JUST NOT
EXPLAINING MYSELF WELL ENOUGH.
IT'S NOT THAT I'VE
FORGOTTEN HOW TO DRIVE IT.
IT'S THAT I'M LOSING
CONFIDENCE IN MY ABILITIES.
MY HEAD FEELS LIKE
A JUMBLED MESS RIGHT NOW
AND THE PANIC
IS REALLY STARTING TO SET IN.
- I HOPE THE DRIVE WASN'T BAD.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO COME
ALL THE WAY TO SAITAMA.
- NAH. THIS PLACE REALLY ISN'T
THAT FAR AWAY FROM SHIBUKAWA.
SO, DON'T SWEAT IT.
AND WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
SAITAMA AND GUNMA ARE RIGHT
NEXT TO EACH OTHER,
SO, IT'S COOL.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE IT
WHEN YOU'RE ON THE TRAINS.
BUT IF YOU'RE IN A
CAR, IT'S PRETTY CLOSE.
- I GUESS. I'M JUST GLAD
YOU'RE HERE.
- YOU CAN CALL ME ANYTIME,
SAY THE WORD AND I'LL
COME RIGHT BACK OUT.
I'M USUALLY NOT
DOING ANYTHING,
SO VISITING YOU IS JUST
A BIG BRIGHT SPOT
IN OTHERWISE BORING DAY.
- YOU DON'T HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
I FIGURED YOU WOULD.
- 'COURSE, I DON'T.
YOU KNOW ME, RIGHT?
( laughs )
- SO... UH... WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- HUH?
- YOU GOT YOURSELF
A BOYFRIEND?
- AH...
LIKE A STEADY ONE?
NO, I GUESS I DON'T.
- ( exclaims ) OH, YEAH?
THAT'S SO AWESOME.
AH, I DIDN'T MEAN
IT'S AWESOME THAT YOUR ALONE.
I MEAN PLAYING THE SINGLE
SCENE, I GET IT, COOL.
- MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED MUCH AFTER ALL.
- ( chuckles)
SEE I TOLD YOU, MY BUDDIES
ARE ALWAYS TELLING ME
HOW THEY THINK
I'M NEVER GONNA GROW UP.
- I DON'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
I MEAN YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
THE KIND OF PERSON WHO
DOESN'T HIDE YOUR FEELINGS,
AND I STILL SEE THAT IN YOU.
- YEAH, THEY SAY THAT, TOO.
THAT YOU CAN TELL EVERYTHING
FROM MY BIG DUMB FACE.
- I LIKE YOUR FACE AND I THINK
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
I CAN TELL THAT YOU'RE NOT
HIDING ANYTHING FROM ME.
REALLY PUTS ME AT EASE.
YOU'RE LIKE AN OLD COMFY CHAIR.
- WELL, THANKS.
I GUESS THERE'S NOT REALLY TOO
MUCH I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
MAYBE GET A FACE TRANSPLANT.
( laughs )
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- ( sighs )
OKAY, WORK STUFF ASIDE,
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
TAKUMI'S THE MOST
SKILLED DRIVER I KNOW.
IT SHOULD BE CAKE FOR HIM
TO MASTER ANY CAR.
AN FR, A FOUR-WHEEL DRIVE,
WHATEVER. WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
- MAYBE IT'S SOME DRIVER
THING WE CAN'T EVEN
WRAP OUR HEADS AROUND.
WE'RE NOT ON THAT LEVEL.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSE TO KNOW?
- WELL, ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
BUNTA'S BUMPED TAKUMI'S
TRAINING UP A PRETTY BIG NOTCH.
I JUST HOPE HE KNOWS
WHAT HE'S DOING.
- SO, KAZUMI, I WAS THINKING
WE COULD HEAD ON UP
TO THAT MOUNTAIN PASS
THAT TAKUMI AND WATARU
RACED ON THE OTHER NIGHT.
I WANNA GIVE THAT SUCKER A
RUN WITH MY OWN SET OF WHEELS,
SEE WHAT KINDA DAMAGE
I CAN DO.
- YEAH, SURE. BUT THAT'S
A WAY DIFFICULT COURSE.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
- YEP. IT'LL TAKE A REAL MAN
TO GO UP AGAINST IT'S CURVES
AND STRAIGHTEN 'EM OUT.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( exclaims )
EITHER I'M TOO BUSY TRYING
TO WORK OUT THE STEERING
OR I CAN'T SEEM TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE THE LINE
IS ON THIS ROAD.
- WHOA. JUST WHAT I'D EXPECT
FROM A TURBO TUNED CAR.
- ( gasps )
- ( tires screeching )
- A LAGGY TURBO. REMINDS
ME OF THE OLD DAYS
OF RIDING SHOTGUN IN MY
BROTHER'S LEVIN.
- MAN, IT IS A HARD RUN.
A LOT HARDER THAN WHAT
WE GOT BACK IN AKINA.
I'M NOT IN MY GROOVE HERE.
- SAY WHAT YOU WANT, BUT
YOU'VE GOTTEN A LOT BETTER
SINCE THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU.
I FEEL SO COMFORTABLE
WITH YOU DRIVING ME AROUND.
- ( chuckles ) ALL RIGHT.
MIGHT NOT LOOK LIKE IT, BUT I'VE
BEEN PRACTICING MY TAIL OFF.
WITH A FINICKY TURBO LIKE MINE,
IF YOU DON'T PRACTICE,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
TRADE HER IN FOR A TRUCK.
- ( tires screeching )
- CRAP. WHY CAN'T I DO THIS?
- Bunta: OH, YEAH, TAKUMI REALLY
SAID THAT, HUH? WELL, NO SHIT.
- Yuichi: IS THAT ALL
YOU GOTTA SAY?
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO THIS
TIME, BUNTA? I'M CURIOUS.
- IT'LL TAKE TOO
LONG TO EXPLAIN,
SO I WON'T GO INTO DETAILS.
BASICALLY, I JUST WANT THE KID
TO EXPERIENCE THE POTENTIAL
NEW CARS HAVE THESE DAYS.
HE NEEDS TO STAY UP ON IT.
- I GUESS I FAILED TO SEE
THE POINT IN THAT.
THE KID'S BEEN RACING PLENTY
OF NEWER CARS TILL NOW.
HE SEEMS TO BE DOING FINE TO ME.
- NAH, I DON'T THINK
HE REALLY GETS IT.
HIS TECHNIQUE IS BASED
COMPLETELY ON THE EIGHT-SIX.
THAT'S ALWAYS BEEN HIS GAME.
YOU SAID HE WAS GOING
ON ABOUT NOT KNOWING
HOW TO DRIVE THE EIGHT-SIX.
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT'S KNOCKING
AROUND IN THAT SKULL OF HIS.
- THEN WHAT'S THE ISSUE?
- HE'S JUST DISHING THAT
STUFF OUT AS AN EXCUSE.
THE TRUTH IS,
HE KNOWS HE'S ABOUT TO GIVE UP
ON THE EIGHT-SIX,
AND HE DOESN'T WANT TO FACE
THE MUSIC LIKE A BIG BOY.
STILL IT'S JUST WHAT
I EXPECTED HIM TO DO.
- YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF
HAVING TAKUMI SWITCH CARS
OVER TO THE IMPREZA?
THAT'S NOT HIS STYLE.
- I WOULDN'T DO THAT. THE
IMPREZA'S MY CAR. I BOUGHT IT.
IT'LL TAKE TIME, BUT HE
NEEDS TO JUMP THIS HURDLE.
IF HE CAN'T, HE'LL NEVER BE THE
KIND OF DRIVER HE WANTS TO BE.
- I WONDER WHAT NATSUKI'S
UP TO THESE DAYS.
HAVEN'T TALKED TO
HER IN A WHILE.
BUT IF I KNOW HER,
SHE NEVER GETS LONELY.
I'VE BEEN GOING FULL TILT,
NO TIME FOR ANYTHING
BUT FOR WHAT I GOT GOING ON
WITH D THAT WEEK.
BUT, IT JUST FEELS OUT OF WHACK.
MAYBE IT'S ME. MAYBE I'M THE
ONE WHO'S OUT OF IT LATELY.
I JUST CAN'T KEEP
MY MIND OFF THAT GIRL.
WHY AM I SO LONELY?
THE RIDE'S REALLY NOT ALL
THAT DIFFERENT
FROM UP THROUGH THIS POINT
IN THE COURSE.
BUT FROM HERE ON OUT,
EVERYTHING IS.
I GOTTA ADMIT THIS IS KILLER.
THE STABILITY IS ROCK SOLID
EVEN IN THIS RAIN. IT'S BADASS.
- MY COUSIN IN HIGASHI-MATSUYAMA
DRIVES A SILVER ALTEZZA.
IT'S A SWEET RIDE.
ANYWAY, HE LET ME
DRIVE IT ONE TIME,
AND THAT WAS ONE HELL OF A CAR.
- HMM-MM.
ALTEZZA'S ARE NICE. NOT MY
FAVORITE, BUT PRETTY COOL.
- ( cellphone vibrating )
- WHAT? YOU'RE NOT ANSWERING?
- I'M GONNA LET THAT ONE
GO TO VOICEMAIL.
IT'S REALLY NOT THAT IMPORTANT.
- COOL.
SHE MUST NOT WANT ANYONE
INTERRUPTING OUR SWEET DATE.
- Man: HURRY UP!
HOW LONG YOU GONNA MAKE ME WAIT,
YOU FREAKING DUMBASS?
C'MON, I DON'T HAVE ALL DAY!
- I'M VERY SORRY ABOUT
KEEPING YOU WAITING, SIR.
WILL THIS ALL BE ON ONE CHECK?
- HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO
TELL YOU SEPARATE CHECKS?
- NICE. THEY'RE DRIVING LANCER
EVOLUTIONS, CHECK IT OUT.
- HEY, I GOT AN IDEA. IF I
PROMISE TO BE REALLY CAREFUL,
DO YOU THINK I CAN DRIVE
YOUR LEVIN TONIGHT?
I'M A DRIVER ON PAPER, BUT
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN BEHIND
A WHEEL IN FOREVER
AND IF I DON'T PRACTICE SOON,
I'M GONNA TOTALLY FORGET HOW.
- WELL, YEAH. SURE.
OF COURSE, YOU CAN!
I'LL COACH YOU THROUGH IT!
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( tires screeching )
- THERE'S GOT TO BE AWAY
I CAN BEAT THAT IMPREZA
WITH THE EIGHT-SIX.
BUT WHAT IS IT?
- ( engine revving )
- THE MORE I DRIVE,
THE MORE CONFUSED I GET.
- ( tires screeching )
- MAN, I CAN'T EVEN
REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I SPUN OUT LIKE THAT.
DAMN IT, WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH ME?
I COULD RUN THIS OVER
MY HEAD A MILLION TIMES
AND I STILL WOULDN'T KNOW
HOW TO PASS THE IMPREZA
IN THE EIGHT-SIX.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I THOUGHT I'VE PUSHED THIS BABY
TO HER LIMITS. MAYBE I HAVE.
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO PUSH HER EVEN FURTHER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW, BUT IF
I WANT TO KEEP RACING,
I DON'T HAVE A WHOLE
LOT OF CHOICE.
AND IF I CAN'T DO
SOMETHING AS SIMPLE AS THAT,
I DON'T DESERVE TO BE
A DRIVER WITH PROJECT D.
- HMM? IF YOU ARE LOOKING
FOR KAZUMI,
I THINK SHE'S HANGING OUT
WITH HER FRIEND OF HERS.
- OH. YOU GOT ANY PROBLEM IF I
JUST WAIT AROUND HERE FOR HER?
I GOT SOME THINGS I HAVE TO SAY.
IF I DON'T, I THINK
I MIGHT REGRET IT
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
- ( cellphone vibrating )
- MY BROTHER CALLING.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- ( gasps )
- WELL, I DON'T CARE WHAT HE
SAID TO YOU. SAY I'M BUSY.
SEND HIM HOME, WATARU.
I DON'T CARE.
I'M HANGING UP, BYE.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL? YOU GOT
SOME PROBLEMS BACK HOME?
- NO. IT'S JUST MY IDIOT
BROTHER BEING DUMB.
- ( chuckles ) GOTCHA.
- THIS IS SUCH CRAP, MAN.
ITSUKI'S, OF ALL PEOPLE,
IS OUT ON AN ALL DAY DATE
AND HERE I AM DRIVING AROUND
WITH YOU ON A SATURDAY NIGHT.
- YOU TOOK THE WORDS RIGHT
OUT OF MY MOUTH, BUDDY.
- LOOK!
- WHOA, WHAT IS IT, A COP?
- BACK THERE AT THAT
CONVENIENCE STORE.
LOOKED A LOT LIKE ITSUKI'S
LEVIN PARKED IN THE LOT.
- EH, SO, HE DECIDED TO
BRING HIS DATE UP HERE
FOR SOME ROMANCE.
WELL...
- SOMETHING SEEMS OFF
ABOUT THIS.
- AWKWARD, RIGHT? WEIRD.
- IF YOU'RE READY TO
HEAD ON BACK HOME,
I'LL BE HAPPY TO TAKE YOU.
- ITSUKI, WHAT IF I DIDN'T
WANT TO GO HOME TONIGHT?
- ( both gasps )
- DUDE, DID YOU HEAR
WHAT SHE JUST SAID TO HIM?
- THE WORDS ANY MAN WOULD
DREAM OF HEARING JUST ONCE
IN HIS LONELY LIFE.
- HOLD UP, MAN,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- WAIT, IF SHE DOESN'T WANT TO
GO HOME THAT COULD ONLY MEAN...
THAT'S WHY SHE'S SEEMS ALL
FLUSTERED AND SWEATY AND WEIRD.
MAYBE WE COULD, I MEAN IF YOU
WANT TO... WHY DON'T WE, UH...
WE COULD GO TO A HOTEL.
- ( gasps )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE SAID THAT TO HER.
- THERE'S NO WAY THIS WILL WORK.
I TELL YA, THIS WHOLE THING
SMELLS LIKE IT'S GONNA
BLOW UP ANY SECOND, AND
I DON'T MEAN IN A GOOD WAY.
- Kazumi: OKAY.
- ( gasps )
- DUDE, PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
- BUT FIRST...
I HAVE SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
I JUST NEED TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GETTING
INTO WITH ME.
THIS IS TOO OPEN.
MIND IF WE STEP AROUND THE
CORNER FOR SOME PRIVACY?
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
- LOOK, I FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
OKAY.
THERE'S THIS GUY
THAT I WAS DATING,
AND WE ONLY BROKE UP
ONLY ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
I STILL... I STILL FEEL
KINDA CONFUSED ABOUT HIM,
LIKE MAYBE I NEVER KNEW
HOW I FELT ABOUT THE GUY.
BUT I THINK WITH YOU, I GUESS
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS THAT
I ALL READY FEEL SO MUCH CLOSER
TO YOU THAN I EVER WAS WITH HIM,
THAT WHEN I'M WITH YOU,
IT'S LIKE HE NEVER EXISTED.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN
ACCEPT THAT BUT IF YOU CAN...
THEN I'D REALLY LIKE
TO BE WITH YOU.
- WHEN YOU SAY DATING,
DOES THAT MEAN THAT YOU
AND THIS GUY WENT TO, UH...
I MEAN... DID YOU AND HIM
GO TO HOTELS TOGETHER...
NOT THAT IT'S MY BUSINESS.
( screams )
SO, WHEN YOU NOD LIKE THAT,
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN YOU WENT
HOTELS WITH THIS GUY, LIKE...
LIKE WHAT, HOW MANY TIMES?
MORE THAN 10? LESS?
- WELL, PROBABLY A FEW MORE.
- ( screams )
- HANG ON, MAN.
IT MIGHT SHOCK YOU AT FIRST
BUT YOU CAN MAKE IT THROUGH,
IT'LL BE WORTH IT.
- IT'S NO BIGGIE. IF YOU'VE
CHANGED YOUR MIND
ABOUT LIKING ME, I GET IT.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
PROMISE, IT'S REALLY NOT.
- ( car approaching )
- HEY!
- YOU'RE A PAIN
IN THE ASS TO FIND.
- HEY, WATARU.
- LET'S GET OUTTA HERE, ITSUKI.
THERE'S NO POINT IN US
STICKING AROUND.
- KAZUMI, WOULD YOU
WAIT A SECOND?
YOU CAN'T KEEP RUNNING AWAY!
- HOW IS THIS ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS?
- IT'S MY BUSINESS 'CAUSE I
KNOW YOU BETTER THAT THIS.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU
OWE HIM AN EXPLANATION
INSTEAD OF LEAVING YOUR
PHONE OFF ALL DAMN DAY?
- KAZUMI, WILL YOU PLEASE HEAR
ME OUT THIS ONE LAST TIME?
- YOU CAN'T SHOW UP OUT OF
NOWHERE AND PULL THIS CRAP.
I'M OLD ENOUGH
TO LEAD MY OWN LIFE.
- HEAR ME OUT AND
I WILL LEAVE YOU ALONE.
JUST LISTEN.
I WANNA TRY THINGS OUT
WITH YOU AGAIN.
AND IF WE'RE GONNA DO THAT
YOU NEED TO KNOW
THERE'S A REASON I WAS
ACTING THE WAY I WAS.
I JUST DIDN'T HAVE
ANY CONFIDENCE.
I MEAN IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVE THE
BEST JOB AND I'M SO MUCH OLDER.
I ASSUMED THAT A BEAUTIFUL
YOUNG GIRL LIKE YOU
WITH SO MUCH TO OFFER,
THAT YOU'D LOSE
INTEREST IN ME,
MOVE ON TO SOMEONE CLOSER
TO YOUR AGE.
THAT'S WHY I ACTED LIKE
I DIDN'T TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
LIKE I DIDN'T TAKE
YOU SERIOUSLY.
BUT THAT'S NOT
HOW I REALLY FEEL.
BEING AWAY FROM YOU,
IT'S HELPED ME REALIZE
HOW MUCH YOU MEAN TO ME.
IT'S COMPLETELY OPENED MY EYES.
I NEED YOU IN MY LIFE, KAZUMI.
- WHAT'S THIS JACKASS DOING?
INTERRUPTING OUR DATE
WITH THIS CRAP.
TOO LATE, PAL, SHE'S
TOTALLY IN LOVE WITH ME
OR DIDN'T YOU NOTICE!
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS.
- LISTEN, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME.
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU
GOTTA TO DO. I'M COOL.
JUST BE HONEST
WITH YOURSELF, OKAY?
THE ONLY THING YOU
NEED TO DO NOW
IS JUMP INTO THE ARMS
OF THE ONE GUY YOU REALLY LIKE.
- YOU ALWAYS SAY
THE RIGHT THING.
- ( gasps )
- AND IT ALL GOES BOOM.
- MAN, IT SUCKS TO BE HIM.
- THINK WE SHOULD
DO SOMETHING?
- WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSE TO DO?
YOU THINK US JUMPING
OUT AND HUGGING HIM
IS GONNA MAKE
FEEL ANY BETTER?
HAVE A LITTLE MERCY ON THE POOR
GUY. WE'LL JUST BAIL QUIETLY.
- ( Itsuki crying )
- OH, ITSUKI,
ARE YOU ACTUALLY CRYING?
I KNOW THAT KINDA PAIN
ALL TOO WELL, MY FRIEND.
- ( crying loudly )
- ( gasps )
- ( exclaims loudly )
- ( tires screeching )
- NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
EVERYTHING JUST SUCKS!
WHAT DO I DO? NONE OF THIS IS
MAKING ANY SENSE TO ME AT ALL!
- ( signing in Japanese )
♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON,
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪