- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
- ♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ( cars approaching )
- Man: WELL, FUGIWARA,
I HATE TO BE THE ONE
TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT JUST BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
YOU AND YOUR LITTLE
CREW OVER THERE
ARE IN FOR A WORLD OF HURT.
MY BUDDY DIDN'T APPRECIATE YOUR
BOY YELLING AT HIM
AND HE MAY HAVE
GONE OFF THE DEEP END.
MAYBE YOU DON'T TRY SO HARD
TO WIN THIS THING.
- WHY DON'T YOU
JUST SAY IT, MAN.
EITHER I TAKE A DIVE TONIGHT OR
MY FRIENDS GET BEATEN UP.
- DON'T GO PUTTIN' WORDS
IN MY MOUTH, KIDDO.
I'M JUST TRYIN' TO DO THE
NEIGHBORLY THING HERE,
THAT'S ALL.
I'M JUST SAYING THERE'S A LOT
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
THAN WINNING...
LIKE BEING ABLE TO WALK.
- THEY'RE CLOSE, MAN.
SOUNDS LIKE THEY'RE JUST
AROUND THE CORNER.
- WE'RE 'BOUT TO GET A GOOD IDEA
HOW THE RACE IS GONNA SHAPE UP.
THAT CORNER IS ONE OF THE
TOUGHEST SPOTS ON THIS COURSE.
IT'S ALL SMOOTH SAILIN'
AT FIRST,
BUT RIGHT AFTER THOSE
SOFT CURVES UP TOP
THERE'S A HARD LEFT.
YOU CAN'T BRAKE WORTH A DAMN
'CAUSE YOU CAN'T DRAW
A STRAIGHT LINE.
- LET'S SEE HOW THE TOP
GUNMA DOWNHILL RACER DOES.
SERIOUSLY I DON'T THINK
THIS GUY GOT A PRAYER.
I MEAN, C'MON, HIS RIDE
ISN'T EVEN EQUIPPED WITH AN ABS.
- ( tires screeching )
- DAMN! THE HELL IS
HE THINKIN'.
HE'S ALREADY MISSED
HIS BRAKING POINT.
- HE'S GUNNIN' IT LIKE
A BAT OUTTA HELL!
UNREAL! DUDE, NO ONE TAKES THAT
CORNER GOIN' THAT FAST!
- ( tires screeching )
- SWEET!
- NO WAY! THE EIGHT SIX
IS RIGHT ON TOP OF HIM!
- DAMMIT.
- YEAH. LOUD N' CLEAR. THANKS.
WORD FROM THE PEANUT GALLERY IS
HE'S REALLY FLYIN' OUT THERE.
TAKUMI'S BRAKING TECHNIQUE
HAS EVERYBODY WOWED.
- HEY, WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
OUR BOY'S BEEN
PRACTICING HIS ASS OFF...
PUSHIN' HIS BRAKING TECHNIQUE
TO IT'S LIMIT
OUGHTTA BE SECOND NATURE BY NOW,
DONCHA YOU'D THINK?
AFTER ALL, IT'S TAKUMI
WE'RE TALKIN' ABOUT HERE,
THE KID'S A GENIUS.
- CONSIDER WHAT HE'S
UP AGAINST, THOUGH.
THE EIGHT SIX'S BRAKE SYSTEM
HAS BEEN FINE-TUNED
WITH AN EMPHASIS
ON THE FRONT END,
FOR DOWNHILL AS OPPOSED TO
FLAT-ROAD BRAKING, YES.
AND BY TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
THE CAR'S LIGHT WEIGHT,
IT IS POSSIBLE,
DEPENDING ON THE DRIVER'S SKILL,
FOR THE BRAKES TO PERFORM BETTER
THAN AN ABS, I'LL GRANT YOU.
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER,
THE EVO SIX CAN ACCELERATE LIKE
CRAZY OUT OF THOSE CORNERS.
IT WON'T TAKE MUCH FOR TAKUMI
TO GET LEFT BEHIND.
THE BEST WAY FOR HIM TO CLOSE
THE GAP IS TO APPRECIATE
WHERE HIS OPPONENT TAKES HIS OWN
BRAKING STYLE FOR GRANTED.
- THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO KEEP IT
LOW-KEY, LITTLE MAN.
HEY, IF YOU WANT TO BE THE HERO
GO RIGHT ON AHEAD,
JUST DON'T CRY OVER WHAT
HAPPENS TO YOUR BUDDIES.
CRAP!
DOESN'T MATTER ANYWAY.
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO
SHAKE HIM OFF
ONCE WE GET TO THE HIGH-SPEED
SECTION IN THE MIDDLE.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT
YOUR PRECIOUS LITTLE EIGHT SIX
ONCE I'M DONE EMBARRASSING YOU!
- ( engine revving )
- HEY, KEISUKE.
SO, JUST BEFORE THEY STARTED,
THE GUY TAKUMI'S RACING SAID
SOMETHING I THINK
YOU WANT TO HEAR.
- Keisuke: YOU'RE KIDDING.
- 'FRAID NOT, MAN.
CHANCES ARE THE GUY WAS JUST
TRYIN' TO BLUFF HIS WAY
OUT OF A FAIR FIGHT,
BUT YOU NEVER KNOW. WE MIGHT BE
IN FOR A FULL-ON BRAWL.
- WELL IT WOULDN'T SURPRISE ME.
THEY'RE ALL JUST A
BUNCH OF THUGS.
- THIS IS
UN-FRIGGIN'-BELIEVABLE!
HOW FAR ARE THOSE LOSERS GONNA
TRY AND PUSH THIS?
LET'S ROUND UP SOME TROOPS OF
OUR OWN AND GO AT THESE ASSHOLES
WITH EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT!
YOU KNOW IT'D ONLY TAKE
A PHONE CALL, KEISUKE.
- FORGET IT, DUDE. CALM DOWN.
- CALM DOWN?
- I THINK MATSUMOTO'S RIGHT.
THE GUY WAS PROBABLY BLUFFIN'.
- MAYBE, BUT WHAT IF HE
WAS SERIOUS?
SUPPOSE THESE JERKS
HAVE BACKUP ON THE WAY.
WE'RE GONNA GET
OUR ASSES KICKED!
I'M NOT TRYING TO GET
BEAT DOWN TONIGHT.
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
HEY, C'MON, MAN, I'M ONLY
KIDDIN', ALL RIGHT?
JUST LIGHTEN UP.
- I CAN KEEP UP, NO PROBLEM.
HE'S NOT BAD, BUT
I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA LOOSE.
IT'S NOT THE CAR
I NEED TO WORRY ABOUT,
IT'S THE DRIVER.
AND HEY IT'S NOT LIKE THIS GUY
IN THE SAME LEAGUE AS DAD.
( scoffing )
NOW THAT WAS TOUGH.
COMPARED TO HIM, THIS TOOL
BRAKES LIKE SOMEBODY'S GRANDMA.
I THINK, I GOT IT! I THINK I
KNOW WHAT HIS WEAKNESS NOW.
YEAH, IT'S OBVIOUS!
- Fumihiro: BUT DOES IT MATTER?
EVEN IF HE WAS BLUFFING,
FOR TAKUMI TO HAVE THAT IDEA
PLANTED INTO HIS HEAD
AT THE STARTING LINE,
I KNOW IT'D THROW ME
OFF MY GAME.
IT'S A PRETTY DAMN EFFECTIVE
TACTIC FOR TIPPING THE SCALE
IN THEIR FAVOR,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
- 'COURSE I WOULD...
I TRIED TO TELL HIM TO
JUST FOCUS ON THE ROAD.
BUT I DUNNO, YOU COULD
SEE HE WAS PRETTY SHOOK-UP
BY THE WHOLE THING.
- A SITUATION LIKE THIS WOULD BE
ENOUGH TO THROW ANYBODY.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
WE'RE TALKIN'
COMPLETELY NEW
TERRITORY FOR HIM.
NO WAY IS HE GONNA BE
ABLE TO FOCUS.
- YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
TAKUMI'S NOT NAIVE ENOUGH TO
FALL FOR THAT CRAP.
- I SURE HOPE YOUR RIGHT.
- I AGREE, BRO.
ANYONE WHO'S RACED THE KID KNOWS
HE DOESN'T SCARE THAT EASILY.
SURE, HE MAY COME OFF
AS THE QUIET TYPE,
BUT ONCE HE GETS BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF A CAR,
TAKUMI'S LEVEL OF CONCENTRATION
IS ABOUT AS GOOD AS IT GETS.
IT'S UNGODLY.
- THIS DUDE'S BRAKING
TECHNIQUE SUCKS.
THAT'S THE CHINK IN HIS ARMOR.
- SON OF A BITCH.
THAT HAMSTER-WHEEL PIECE
OF CRAP IS STAYIN ON ME.
MAN, THIS LITTLE
PUNK IS STARTING
TO GET ON MY LAST
FRIGGIN' NERVE!
I GOTTA TAKE IT EASY ON
THIS UPCOMING SECTION.
IF HE SCREWS UP AND SIDE SWIPES
ME THEN WE'RE IN FOR SOME SHIT.
- HIS LINE CHANGED.
LOOKS LIKE THE SPEED I'M
TAKIN' THESE CORNERS AT
HAS GOT THIS JERK
PRETTY SPOOKED.
- THIS IS ONLY A
WORKING HYPOTHESIS,
BUT IF THE EVO SIX WAS TO TAKE
UP A DEFENSIVE POSITION,
ITS ENTRY INTO THE CORNERS WOULD
PROBABLY START GETTING TIGHTER.
GIVEN THAT, IF THE DRIVER
ISN'T ANTICIPATING AN ATTACK
FROM THE OUTSIDE, THAT'S THE
LINE TAKUMI WILL GO WITH.
- THE OUTSIDE IS WIDE OPEN.
THAT'S MY IN.
- THEY'RE HERE? GOOD, GOOD...
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE RACE RIGHT NOW,
SO JUST KEEP 'EM ON STANDBY DOWN
THERE UNTIL IT'S OVER, OKAY?
YEAH, I KNOW. THEY'RE A FREAKY
GROUP OF THUGS AREN'T THEY?
MY ADVICE, TREAT 'EM
WITH CRAZY RESPECT.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
THE CALVARY'S ARRIVED.
- THIS WILL BE EPIC.
- Ryosuke: HE MAY SEEM
LIKE AN AMATEUR,
BUT BY NO MEANS IS THE
EVO SIX'S DRIVER A FOOL.
HE HAS HIS CAR PRETTY
WELL EQUIPPED,
AND YOU CAN BE SURE HE KNOWS
HOW TO USE EVERY MODIFICATION
TO HIS BEST POSSIBLE ADVANTAGE.
IN TERMS OF BRAKING, HE'S
EXPLOITING THE ABS
TO ITS UTMOST.
A WISE MOVE ON HIS PART.
SEE, ABS' ARE
DESIGNED SPECIFICALLY
SO THAT EVEN SOMEONE WITH ONLY A
RUDIMENTARY UNDERSTANDING OF
TIRE TRACTION CAN
BRAKE LIKE A PRO.
THE QUESTION IS,
IF HE'S BECOME SO COMFORTABLE
WITH THE WAY THE CAR HANDLES
WHEN CONDITIONS ARE IDEAL,
CAN HE ADAPT WHEN THEY'RE NOT?
IF HE'S NOT ABLE TO,
THEN, UNDER PRESSURE, WHERE
AND WHEN HE DECIDES TO BRAKE
GOING INTO EACH CORNER CAN PROVE
TO BE HIS BIGGEST LIABILITY.
WHETHER OR NOT TAKUMI
CAN SPOT THAT WEAKNESS
WILL BE THE DECIDING FACTOR
IN THIS RACE.
- TOO SLOW!
- PERSISTENT LITTLE BITCH!
THE HIGH-SPEED SECTION'S COMING
UP. JUST A LITTLE BIT FURTHER.
ONE MORE CORNER AND
I'LL FINISH THIS THING.
- ( tires screeching )
- WHAT THE HELL!
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY TRACTION?
- THIS IS IT.
- CRAP. OIL!
SON OF A BITCH!
I MUST HAVE HIT
SOME LEFT OVER SPILL
HUGGING THE INSIDE TOO TIGHT.
WE'RE NOT AT THE FINISH LINE
YET. I CAN STILL DO THIS.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS PASS THE LUCKY
LITTLE BUTT MUNCH ONE MORE TIME!
THE NEXT SECTION IS WHERE
I'LL MAKE MY MOVE.
THAT EIGHT SIX DOESN'T
HAVE CRAP ON ME, WATCH!
THIS BABY HERE IS THE
FASTEST 2.0-LITER TURBO
ON THE ROAD, ASSHOLE!
NO WAY I'M GONNA LET SOME DINKY,
LITTLE 1.6 SHOW ME UP!
- THEY SHOULD BE ON THE
LAST PART OF THE COURSE.
THE MID-SPEED SECTION WHERE
THE ROAD WIDENS
JUST ENOUGH FOR THEM
TO KICK UP THEIR PACE A NOTCH.
- THAT'S WHERE THE EVO
CAN GET HIM, RIGHT?
- NAH. YOU GOT IT BACKWARDS.
- HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE HIGHER THE SPEED THE
HARDER IS TO KNOW
WHERE TO BRAKE, SO THE RISK
MULTIPLIES BY, LIKE, TENFOLD.
THE DIFFERENCE IN HORSEPOWER'S
NOT GONNA MEAN MUCH.
AM I RIGHT, OR AM I RIGHT, BRO?
- HMM. THINK ABOUT
WHAT I SAID EARLIER.
POWER ALONE IS A POOR SURROGATE
FOR TECHNIQUE IN A DOWNHILL RUN
LIKE THE ONE THEY'RE ON.
- DAMMIT! IT'S NO GOOD.
HE'S GOIN' IN WITHOUT BRAKING?
- ♪ MISSION IMPOSSIBLE ♪
- ( car screeching )
♪ PEOPLE SAY, BABY,
I LOVE DANGER ♪
♪ I GO, NEVER MISS A BEAT ♪
♪ DOWN INSIDE I JUST
FEEL A STRANGER ♪
♪ RUNNIN', RUNNIN', RUNNIN' ♪
♪ LOVE'S BACK IN TOWN ♪
♪ WALKIN' DOWN ♪
♪ CROSSIN' STREETS
INSIDE YOUR HEART ♪
♪ URN AROUND AND FACE IT ♪
♪ NEVER TAKE A CHAIN
TO MY SOUL ♪
♪ MISSION IMPOSSIBLE ♪
♪ EASY AND SIMPLE, GO ♪
♪ SEE THE LIGHT
IN A STORMY SKY ♪
♪ MISSION IMPOSSIBLE ♪
- WHAT THE HELL MAN.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
THAT KID IS SOMETHING ELSE.
- Fumihiro: I SEE.
THANKS FOR THE WARNING.
OKAY GUYS, SOUNDS LIKE
HE WASN'T BLUFFING AFTER ALL.
FIVE OR SIX SUSPICIOUS-LOOKING
CARS ARE HEADED OUR WAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD TO RYOSUKE?
- WELL, I'D SAY OUR
OPPONENTS HAVE DEFAULTED
ON THE NEXT CHALLENGE.
I WANT ALL OF YOU ON HIGH-ALERT.
BE READY TO PULL
OUT AT ANY TIME.
THE SAFETY OF OUR TEAM IS OUR
ONLY CONCERN. SO NO HEROICS, OK?
- YES, SIR.
- RIGHT.
- FUMIHIRO, LISTEN TO ME.
IF IT COMES DOWN TO IT, KEISUKE
AND I WILL DISTRACT THEM.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE THE TEAM, GET
EVERYONE THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
- NO CHANCE, WE'RE JUST NOT
LEAVING YOU HERE.
- IT ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS HAPPENED.
I ASSUME THAT RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THAT RISK
WHEN I FORMED
PROJECT D, NOT YOU.
- YEA DON'T SWEAT IT, DUDE.
I'VE GOT HIS BACK. TRUST ME.
BELIEVE OR NOT I'VE BEEN
IN MY SHARE OF FIGHTS.
I KNOW HOW TO HANDLE MYSELF.
YOU JUST CONCENTRATE ON
GETTING EVERYONE ELSE OUT.
- IF THAT'S HOW YOU WANT IT.
YOU'RE A DAMN GOOD FRIEND AND
ONE HELL OF A BROTHER, KEISUKE.
I HOPE YOU KNOW THAT.
- PLEASE, YOU GOTTA LET
ME GO OUT THERE
AND THROW DOWN WITH YOU.
- HOW 'BOUT I JUST
KICK YOUR ASS?
- KINDA TRYIN' TO AVOID THAT.
- PROMISE ME YOUR NOT GONNA
LET THEM HURT, RYOSUKE.
I WANT YOU TO GIVE ME YOUR WORD.
- YOU'VE GOT IT, MAN.
NO WORRIES.
- I'M GONNA STAY BEHIND
WITH YOU GUYS?
- I APPRECIATE THAT, BUT NO,
WE'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
- ( vehicles approaching )
- HERE THEY COME.
- EVERYBODY GET IN VANS
ONE AND TWO, IMMEDIATELY!
- NOTHIN' LIKE A LITTLE
TAILGATE PARTY, EH?
( laughing )
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE PRETTY BOY
BALLIN' LIKE A BABY GIRL.
- OH, NO QUESTION. WHATDYA SAY
YOU GUYS WANT TO JUMP IN
AND GIVE THESE GUYS A HAND
WITH THE BEAT DOWN?
WE'RE OUT OF CRAP TON
OF MONEY EITHER WAY
MIGHT AS WELL ENJOY THIS.
SHIT. I COULDA PAID OFF MY
CAR WITH THE CASH I LOST
ON THIS RACE I'M TAKIN' IT
OUT OF SOMEBODY'S ASS.
- HELLS YEAH. I AM RIGHT
THERE WITH YOU, MAN.
BESIDES, WHO'S GONNA STOP US
FROM GETTING A COUPLE OF PUNCHES
WHILE A WHOLE BUNCH OF
BIKER POUND THESE GUYS
INTO LUNCH MEAT.
- I'M SURE THEY WON'T MIND US
HAVING A LITTLE FUN.
- ( all laughing )
- ( gasping ) HOLY CRAP.
LOOK AT THIS GUY!
- I HEAR THE GANG HE
USED TO LEAD
RAN THE NORTHERN KATOU REGION'S
UNDERGROUND WITH AN IRON FIST.
HE'S KNOWN ALL OVER AS THE DUDE
YOU DO NOT WANT TO CROSS.
- UH-HUH.
- JUST SIT TIGHT, BRO.
I'LL HANDLE THIS.
- ( laughing )
- ( gasping )
- I HAD A FEELIN' IT'D BE YOU.
- HUH?
- MY BAD, K-DOG.
IT'S SO DARK OUT HERE I
ALMOST DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YA.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN, SIR.
- WHY THE HELL IS A GUY LIKE YOU
HANGING OUT WITH THESE LOSERS?
FRIENDS HARD TO COME BY THESE
DAYS, OR WHAT?
- NO, I UH...
I'M JUST ON THE CLOCK, YA KNOW,
IT'S NOT LIKE I RUN WITH 'EM.
THIS IS STRICTLY
A THIRD-PARTY THING.
- ( gulping )
- NOW THAT I'M HERE, THOUGH,
LOOKS LIKE THESE JERKOFFS
HAVE BEEN DISRESPECTING YOU.
AM I RIGHT?
- ( gasping in fear )
- KINDA, YEAH. BUT AS FAR AS
ME AND MY BOYS ARE CONCERNED,
IT'S ALL WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE.
NOW YOU WANNA GET THOSE
CARS OUT OF OUR WAY
OR DO I HAVE TO SAY PLEASE?
- DAMN, ARE WE IN YOUR WAY?
MY BAD.
- YOU HEARD THE MAN! MOVE 'EM!
- YES, SIR!
- ( grunting )
- ( all exclaiming in fear )
- HOW THE HELL DID YOU
PULL THAT OFF?
DON'T TELL ME YOU
ACTUALLY KNOW THOSE GUYS.
- YEAH WELL,
WHAT CAN I SAY, MAN?
I DIDN'T ALWAYS HANG
WITH SOCIALITES LIKE YOU.
THE BIG GUY WAS A
BUD OF MY FROM WAY BACK.
WELL, NOW THAT I THINK OF IT HE
WAS MORE LIKE MY LITTLE BROTHER.
- HIM? YOUR JUNIOR?
- HEY, I COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHO HE WAS TO YOU.
WE DODGED A MAJOR BULLET.
FOR A MINUTE THERE I
THOUGHT WE WERE ALL
GONNA GET OUR ASSES KICKED.
BUT THANKS TO THAT ACT JUST NOW,
NOT A SINGLE ONE OF GOT SO
MUCH AS A NOSE BLEED.
I HOPE YOU REALIZE HOW GLAD
WE ARE YOU'RE ON OUR SIDE.
- DUMB SON OF A BITCH.
YOU CALL US OUT HERE
JUST TO EMBARRASS ME?
NOBODY TANGLES WITH THE
TAKAHASHI BROTHERS.
NOBODY WHO KNOWS WHAT KINDA
CRAZY BASTARD KEISUKE IS!
- ( gasping in fear )
- PROJECT D'S REP CASTS
A LONG SHADOW, PAL.
EVERYBODY THAT LIVES WITHIN
A HUNDRED KILOMETERS OF GUNMA
THINKS OF 'EM AS LIVIN' LEGENDS.
YOU WANT TO TAKE A GUESS
WHERE I'M FROM,
OR CAN YOU READ A
LICENSE PLATE?
- ( stutters ) I'M SORRY, MAN.
I HAD NO IDEA.
YOU GOTTA BELIEVE ME.
THIS WAS JUST A HUGE MISTAKE!
- IF WE'D KNOWN YOU WERE A
GUNMA MAN,
WE WOULDA NEVER BOTHERED YOU.
- IT WAS JUST AN HONEST MIX-UP
ON OUR PART, SIR.
NO NEED TO GET ANGRY.
- OH I SEE, YOU TRYIN' TO
TELL ME HOW I SHOULD ACT NOW?
YOU ASSWIPES GOT A HARD LESSON
IN MANNERS COMIN' AT YA
BEFORE TONIGHT'S OVER.
SIT THE HELL DOWN!
- WE'D LIKE TO CANCEL
THE TIMED TRIALS.
AS YOU KNOW KEISUKE'S FD
CAN'T PERFORM UP TO SPECS
AND I'M CERTAIN UNDER
THE CIRCUMSTANCES
- YOU'RE PERFECTLY OK WITH THAT?
- YES, YES! WE'RE FINE
WITH THAT! SURE!
- ALRIGHT, THEN. LET'S MOVE 'EM
OUT, GUYS. TIME TO GO HOME.
- YES! AS OF TONIGHT, PROJECT D
OWNS THE SAITAMA RACING SCENE!
- ♪ I FEEL READY TO GO
AND SHINE AGAIN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT FOR YOU ♪
♪ I WANNA SPEND MY TIME
IN A BETTER WAY ♪
♪ RUNNIN' AWAY FROM YOU ♪
♪ I WOULD FLY IN THE SKY,
I WOULD FLY IN THE SKY ♪
- ( car speeding )
♪ I WOULD FLY IN THE SKY
FOR A NIGHT OR MORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DESERVE
TO LIVE MY LIFE ♪
♪ SAY WHAT I WANT,
DREAM FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ FREEDOM IS IN MY HEART ♪
♪ I WOULD FLY IN THE SKY
FOR A NIGHT OR MORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DESERVE
TO LIVE MY LIFE ♪
- I LEARNED A LOT
OUT THERE TONIGHT.
I'VE GOT A LOT BETTER IDEA
OF WHAT'S COMIN'.
AFTER TONIGHT,
I KNOW WHAT I'VE GOTTA DO.
- ( engine revving )
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪