- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ DOG FIGHT ♪
♪ DOG FIGHT ♪
- ♪ YOU'RE BIG TIME GAMBLER ♪
- ♪ BREAK IT, BREAK IT
STRIKE IT, SHAKE IT ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
- SO NOBUHIKO, DID YOU HEAR?
- ABOUT PROJECT D COMING UP?
I DID. IT'S PRETTY BIG NEWS.
- I MEAN, WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
I'M TOTALLY FREAKING
OUT HERE, MAN.
- I DON'T SEE WHY.
IT ISN'T LIKE THERE'S ANYTHING
FOR US TO BE AFRAID OF.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS,
YOU REALLY DON'T THINK SO?
- NAH, MORE THAN ANYTHING
I'M JUST CURIOUS.
I WANNA SEE IF THIS
FAMOUS TEAM
CAN ACTUALLY LIVE UP TO
THEIR REPUTATION.
I'M ACTUALLY
EXCITED THEY'RE COMING
TO RACE ON OUR HOME COURSE.
SHOULD BE AN ADVENTURE.
DON'T YOU THINK, KYOKO?
HMM.
- YOU KNOW, IF I HAD TO TAKE A
GUESS, I'D SAY YOU WERE OUT HERE
LOOKIN' FOR A SILVER
CELL PHONE. AM I RIGHT?
- OKAY, I'M MIGHT BE
GOING CRAZY, BUT
I THINK I'VE JUST MET
MY MR. RIGHT!
- ( engine starts )
- WAIT, DON'T GO!
- Nobuhiko: KYOKO?
KYOKO, WAKE UP.
- WERE YOU EVEN
LISTENING TO HIM?
OUR NEXT OPPONENT IS PROJECT D,
IT'S A PRETTY BIG DEAL.
- WHAT I WAS SAYING IS THAT WE
WANT YOU TO TAKE THE HILL CLIMB.
THESE DAYS YOU'RE OUR ACE,
YOU DO REALIZE THAT, RIGHT?
- YEAH, OF COURSE I DO. I'LL
STAY FOCUSED AND HIT IT HARD.
JUST LEAVE THAT
HILL CLIMB TO ME.
- DO YOU WANNA KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THE GUY
WHO'S DRIVING AGAINST YOU?
- NOT A CHANCE.
THAT STUFF'LL CLOUD MY HEAD.
I'LL CONCENTRATE BETTER
WITHOUT OUT IT.
THE ONLY THING I CAN
DO IS GET OUT THERE
AND DRIVE THE BEST I KNOW HOW.
- ( engine revving )
- ( tires screeching )
- THIS IS BAD.
THE BATTLE'S TOMORROW AND I'M
NOT IN MY GROOVE AT ALL.
I CAN'T GET EXCITED OVER THIS
ONE LIKE I CAN THE OTHER RACES.
- YEAH. COOL. I GOTCHA.
IT WAS THE GUY FROM
THE BASE PARKING LOT.
- HE SAYS PROJECT D
IS PULLING IN.
- HMM.
I GOT A STRANGE FEELING ABOUT
THIS. SOMETHING WITH THE ENGINE.
MAYBE I'M JUST
IMAGINING IT. I DUNNO.
ALL NIGHT AND TOMORROW I HAVE
TO MAKE SURE MY FOCUS ON
THIS BATTLE AND NOTHING ELSE.
I CAN'T LOSE.
EVEN IF I'M UP AGAINST
THE BEST DRIVER
WE'VE EVER SEEN.
- I'M GONNA BET THIS IS THEM.
- ( engine revs )
- ( gasps )
- DO YOU SEE THE GUY
IN THE YELLOW FD?
THAT'S KEISUKE TAKAHASHI,
PROJECT D'S HILL CLIMBER.
ONE BAD DUDE.
HE'S THE ONE YOU'RE
RACING TOMORROW.
- ( stutters )
KEISUKE TAKAHASHI...
- C'MON, YOU'RE NOT
INTIMIDATED, ARE YOU?
THIS GUY DRIVES AN FD
ALMOST EXACTLY LIKE YOURS.
YOU HAVE A KILLER
DRIVING TECHNIQUE
THAT ANYONE WOULD RECOGNIZE.
SHOW HIM YOUR SKILLS, BE
CONFIDENT AND YOU WILL BE FINE.
- KEISUKE TAKAHASHI...
I CAN'T EVEN THINK STRAIGHT.
IT HAD TO BE LIKE THIS?
JUST MY LUCK.
OF COURSE I HAVE TO FACE
THIS GUY LIKE THIS.
- OKAY. IS IT COOL IF WE
START PRACTICE RUNS?
- ALL RIGHT, GUYS. LET'S ROLL.
I WANT YOU TO DO FIVE RUNS
AT EIGHTY PERCENT.
ONE THING. YOU GUYS
WON'T BE ABLE TO DRIVE
LIKE YOU USUALLY DO, OKAY?
JUST SO YOU KNOW, THIS RUN
WAS CHOSEN SPECIFICALLY
TO TRAIN YOU, KEISUKE.
SO, HIT IT WITH ALL YOU GOT.
- HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- OKAY, YOU'RE READY TO GO.
- LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GOOD
OVER HERE TOO.
- UH.
- THOSE ARE TWO
AMAZING MACHINES.
GIVES ME CHILLS JUST
WATCHING THEM.
- HOW CAN YOU TALK ABOUT THEM
LIKE THEY'RE HOT CHICKS, MAN?
WE'RE GOING HEAD TO HEAD
WITH THOSE CARS TOMORROW NIGHT.
- SO, NOBUHIKO, WHAT DO YOU PLAN
ON DOING BETWEEN NOW AND THEN?
- I'M GONNA WATCH THEIR
EVERY MOVE UNTIL THE SUN IS UP.
I TOOK TOMORROW OFF
FROM WORK.
CHANCES LIKE THIS DON'T
COME ALONG VERY OFTEN.
I'LL SCRUTINIZE EVERY
MOVE THEY MAKE
WHILE THEY TRY TO UNRAVEL
THE INS AND OUTS OF OUR COURSE.
ESTABLISHING ANY KIND OF
PLAN WILL HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL AFTER THAT.
THE TWO DRIVERS FOR
PROJECT D ARE GREAT, NO DOUBT.
BUT IT'S THAT DUDE IN-CHARGE
WHO'S THE TRULY AMAZING ONE.
I HAVE TO FIND THEIR WEAKNESS.
- ( tires screeching )
- THIS COURSE IS
A PAIN IN MY ASS TO DRIVE.
NAH, FUMIHIRO. IT'S TERRIBLE.
THE ASPHALT'S WAVIER
THAN A FREAKIN' RIVER.
MY CAR'LL BE TOSSING
SPARKS ALL OVER
LIKE ONE OF THOSE
OLD F-ONE JOBS.
WE RAISED THE CAR A FEW TIMES,
TRIED LIKE SIX
DIFFERENT SETTINGS,
BUT NOTHING'S COMING
TOGETHER RIGHT.
IT'S ALL STARTING TO
MAKE ME KINDA NERVOUS.
- CHECK OUT TAKUMI'S RIDE.
THE OLD EIGHT-SIX
IS HAVING ISSUES TOO.
I GUESS NOBODY'S SAFE.
OH, YEAH, ONE OTHER THING.
HAVE YOU NOTICED YET?
- NOTICED WHAT?
- REMEMBER THAT CHICK IN
THE BLACK FD WE RAN INTO
THE OTHER DAY WHEN WE CAME OUT
HERE TO SCOUT THE COURSE.
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S A
MEMBER OF THE GROUP
WE'RE GOING UP AGAINST.
- STRANGE. I DIDN'T EVEN
SEE HER WITH 'EM.
- YEAH. SHE COULDN'T TAKE
HER EYES OFF OF YOUR FD
WHEN YOU DROVE OFF.
I'M WONDERING IF
SHE'S THE ONE
WHO'S REPRESENTING THEM
IN THE HILL CLIMB.
THAT COULD MAKE
THINGS INTERESTING.
- I'D SAY THAT'S A VERY
LIKELY POSSIBILITY.
I MEAN THE GIRL
IS DRIVING AN FD, RIGHT?
- WHAT?
- ANYWAY, IT DOESN'T MATTER
TO ME WHO I'M DRIVING AGAINST.
IT COULD BE ANYONE.
TRUTH IS, MY REAL OPPONENT
IS THE COURSE ITSELF.
- Woman: OH MY GOSH!
IT'S LIKE FATE ITSELF SET
YOU GUYS UP TO MEET.
- THERE'S NOTHING
WONDERFUL ABOUT IT.
MORE THAN ANYTHING
I WANNA RUN AWAY.
- WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I MEAN, THIS IS A ONCE IN
A LIFETIME CHANCE.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- YES, I AM. YOU FOUND
A REALLY HOT GUY
WHO'S INTO THE SAME
STUFF AS YOU!
IT'S THE PERFECT CHANCE
TO GET TO KNOW HIM.
- YEAH, YOU THINK SO?
- DO I LOOK LIKE
I'M LYING TO YOU?
YOU'VE GOTTA GET ON THAT
COURSE AND RACE THIS GUY.
IF YOU SHOW HIM WHAT A
GREAT DRIVER YOU ARE,
HE'S FOR SURE GONNA TAKE NOTICE.
IT'S A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
DON'T PASS IT UP.
- HMM.
- I STUCK AROUND UNTIL SUNRISE
WATCHING THEIR TRIAL RUNS,
AND I GOTTA TELL YOU,
THEY'RE NOT FOOLING AROUND.
THESE GUYS ARE GOOD.
ESPECIALLY THAT EIGHT-SIX.
ON THE DOWNHILL,
THAT SUCKER WAS OPERATING WAY
ABOVE WHAT WE'RE USED TO.
LOOK, THE TRUTH IS THAT WE
DON'T HAVE A DOWNHILLER
THAT CAN KNOCK THEM
OFF THE TRACKS,
SO, I'LL RACE THAT LEG,
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU TO
EXPECT TOO MUCH.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE
HILL CLIMB THOUGH,
I THINK OUR TEAM MIGHT BE ABLE
TO KNOCK IT OUT.
THANKS IN NO SMALL
PART TO A LITTLE ACE
IN OUR POCKET CALLED KYOKO.
WE PLAY OUR CARDS RIGHT
AND WE MIGHT ACTUALLY
HAVE A CHANCE AT BEATING THEM.
IT MAY NOT BE MUCH OF A PLAN,
BUT IT'S ALL WE'VE GOT.
WE'RE ALL COUNTING
ON YOU, KYOKO.
- I WON'T LET YOU DOWN.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER BEEN
MORE MOTIVATED FOR A RACE.
- ( air hissing )
- ( gasps )
- ( tires screeching )
- DID YOUR RIDE CRAP OUT ON YOU?
- UH, YEAH, I WAS DRIVING.
AND THE ENGINE DIED ON ME.
- WHAT, JUST OUTTA NOWHERE?
- NO. NOT EXACTLY
OUT OF NOWHERE.
IT'S BEEN RUNNING A
LITTLE SHAKY SINCE, LIKE,
THE DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY,
BUT I DUNNO,
I GUESS I FIGURED
I WAS IMAGINING IT.
THEN JUST A MINUTE AGO ALMOST
ALL THE POWER DROPPED OUT.
I GOT A LITTLE FREAKED OUT
SO I STOPPED.
- HOLD ON.
- WEREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO RACE
ME IN THE HILL CLIMB TONIGHT?
THAT'S YOU RIGHT?
- THAT'S ME.
- BUT WITH MY CAR...
- THIS REALLY SUCKS.
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD TO
RACING ANOTHER FD.
IT SEEMED FAST. YOU SEEMED LIKE
YOU COULD CARRY THE COURSE.
IF YOU THOUGHT SOMETHING
WAS WRONG WITH YOUR CAR,
WHY DIDN'T YOU BOTHER
TO CHECK IT OUT
WHEN THERE WAS STILL LIGHT?
I'M SORRY TO HEAR YOU'D TRY
TO BEAT ME IN A CAR
THAT ISN'T MAINTAINED.
THAT'S JUST SLOPPY.
AND THERE'S NOT ONE EXCITING
THING ABOUT BATTLING A DRIVER
WHO DOESN'T GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT THEIR OWN CAR.
- ( tires screeching )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THAT WAS SO EMBARRASSING.
- WHOA, KYOKO'S FD
BROKE DOWN?
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
SHE WAS STARING AT HER ENGINE
ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
- THAT DOESN'T SOUND GOOD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK WE
SHOULD DO ABOUT IT?
- FIRST, WE GO TAKE A LOOK.
- I FEEL LIKE SUCH A LOSER.
WHY COULDN'T I HAVE JUST
LISTENED TO MY CAR?
IT WAS TRYING TO
TELL ME SOMETHING.
I GOT ALL EXCITED LIKE
SOME STUPID LITTLE GIRL,
AND THIS IS WHAT I GET. NICE.
I WANTED TO RACE SO BAD.
AND MORE THAN ANYTHING,
TO GO UP AGAINST KEISUKE.
IT COULD'VE BEEN PERFECTION.
BUT NOW, HE JUST HATES ME.
- ( car approaching )
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- HEY, YOU'RE CAR'S STILL
GOT SOME JUICE IN IT, RIGHT?
WELL, DON'T JUST STARE AT ME,
PULL IT BACK AROUND.
- CHECK IT. IT'S JUST LIKE
I THOUGHT. PIPING SLIPPED OUT.
THE INTERCOOLER HOSING
MUST HAVE CORRODED.
- CAN YOU FIX IT?
- ISN'T THAT WHY YOU KEEP ME
AROUND? OF COURSE I CAN FIX IT.
WE GOT EVERYTHING WE
NEED RIGHT HERE.
- THEN LET'S GET CRACKING.
I WANNA DO THIS FAST.
- YOU THINK THEY'LL BE
ABLE TO FIX IT.
- I'D BE SURPRISED
IF THEY COULDN'T.
I MEAN, THEY TOOK
EVERY SPARE PART
WE BROUGHT WITH US UP THERE.
- ( chuckles ) YOU KNOW HOW
THOROUGH KEISUKE CAN BE.
- HEY, RYOSUKE.
- HMM?
- DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT THE REASON
YOU CHOSE THIS COURSE
IS BECAUSE YOU WANTED
TO TRAIN KEISUKE?
YOU WEREN'T KIDDING AROUND,
WERE YOU? YOU DID MEAN IT RIGHT?
- COURSE I DID.
KEISUKE ISN'T ONE TO HESITATE
WHEN IT COMES TO STICKING THAT
ACCELERATOR DOWN.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL
YOU HE'S A FIGHTER.
BUT IT CAN WORK AGAINST
HIM SOMETIMES.
IT ISN'T TOO MUCH OF AN ISSUE
WHEN THE COURSE IS SMOOTH.
BUT ON A ROAD
LIKE THIS ONE IT IS.
A FIERCE BATTLING SPIRIT AND
COLDER THAN ICE PEDAL WORK
IS WHAT I WANT FROM HIM.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
BEAT INTO HIS HEAD FOR SO LONG.
- SHE'S NOT HERE. THAT'S WEIRD,
WHERE COULD SHE HAVE GONE?
- ( engine revving )
- THE BOOST IS KICKING IN
JUST WHEN IT SHOULD.
I DON'T WANNA HEAR ANY
MORE ABOUT YOU
NOT GETTING ENOUGH POWER.
- HOW COOL. I WISH I KNEW
HOW TO SAY THANK YOU.
- FORGET ABOUT IT. I DIDN'T
DO THIS TO HEAR A THANK YOU.
I JUST WANT TO SEE YOU GIVE IT
ALL YOU'VE GOT TONIGHT.
- ( engine revving )
- LET'S GET BACK, TOMIGUCHI.
- COOL.
- OH, DON'T TELL ME.
DID HE JUST FIX HER CAR?
- THAT'S GOTTA BE THE COOLEST
THING I'VE EVER SEEN.
- I LIKE HIM. I LIKE HIM SO MUCH
MORE THAN I THOUGHT I COULD.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
- YOU WANNA LEAD FIRST?
- HMM.
- BEING AGGRESSIVE IN THIS
RACE WILL WORK FOR YOU.
BUT IF YOU'RE THINKING
ABOUT STRATEGY,
SHOULDN'T YOU BE CHASING
FOR THE FIRST HEAT?
FROM WHAT I COULD TELL
WATCHING THESE GUYS ROLL,
THAT GUY'S FD ISN'T USED
TO COURSES LIKE THIS ONE.
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU'VE SEEN,
BUT I WANNA DO THIS MY WAY.
I JUST... I HAVE
TO DRIVE IN FRONT.
I NEVER INTRODUCED MYSELF.
MY NAME'S KYOKO IWASE.
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO FINALLY RACE YOU.
- KEISUKE TAKAHASHI,
WITH PROJECT D,
IF YOU COULDN'T GUESS.
- HOLD UP FOR A SEC. I ONLY
HAVE ONE THING TO TELL YOU.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE BATTLE,
IF SOMETHING STRIKES YOU AS ODD,
REMEMBER THIS.
THAT GIRL'S BEHIND A WHEEL
OF A SINGLE TURBINE TURBO.
- HUH? WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- FUMIHIRO, LET'S DO THIS.
- YOU GOT IT.
- ( upbeat song playing )
♪ FLY AWAY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY FROM HERE ♪
- START 'EM UP!
♪ FROM THE EVIL OF THIS TOWN,
THEN I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE SKY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
- GO!
♪ FLY AWAY FROM HERE ♪
♪ FROM THE PRISON OF THIS LIFE,
LET ME TAKE YOU AWAY TONIGHT ♪
♪ FLY AWAY ♪
- COME ON, MAN.
DON'T KEEP IT A SECRET.
I KNOW YOU'VE GOT A
PLAN FOR KYOKO.
YOU'VE GOTTA TELL US.
- IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER ANYMORE.
I'VE KNOWN KYOKO
FOR A LONG TIME.
AND SHE LETS HER EMOTIONS
DO THE DRIVING FOR HER
WHEN SHE GETS ALL WORKED UP.
SHE ALREADY OWES THOSE
GUYS FOR FIXING HER CAR.
MY BET IS THAT NOW
SHE'LL DITCH HER TACTICS
AND JUST TAKE THEM HEAD ON.
THAT'S JUST THE WAY SHE IS.
- THIS CHICK IS GOOD.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT HER I CAN'T PEG.
IS SHE ONE OF THOSE OPPONENTS
THAT'LL GIVE ME A
TOUGH TIME OUT HERE.
I DON'T GET IT. MAYBE
I'M JUST OUT OF IT.
OR MAYBE WE SCREWED
UP HER SETTINGS
WHEN WE JACKED WITH HER RIDE.
- ( tires screeching )
- DON'T FALL INTO HER
PACE, KEISUKE.
COME ON. KEEP COOL, PAL.
YOU GOTTA STAY CALM. I MEAN,
HELL, YOU JUST STARTED THE RACE!
- THIS IS SO DIFFERENT.
I'VE NEVER FELT THIS KIND
OF FULFILLMENT
WHEN DRIVING ON THE
MOUNTAIN PASS BEFORE.
I KNOW I CAN'T BEAT HIM,
NO MATTER WHAT I DO.
BUT I DON'T CARE.
I JUST WANT HIM TO WATCH ME.
I WANT HIM TO SEE ME
DRIVING MY BEST.
THAT'S WHY I
WANTED TO LEAD.
I HAVE HIS UNDIVIDED ATTENTION,
IF ONLY FOR A MOMENT.
FOR NOW, IT'S ALL ON ME.
I LOVE IT!
WATCH ME, MY DARLING. THIS IS
ME. THIS IS WHAT I CAN DO.
- I'M SURPRISED, GIRL.
YOU'RE A FAST ONE.
I BLEW YOU OFF BEFORE
'CUZ I FIGURED YOU WERE
JUST SOME CHICK.
BUT THAT WAS MY BAD.
RIGHT NOW, ALL I SEE IS ONE
TOP-NOTCH ROTARY DRIVER.
BUT NOW THAT I SEE YOU
FOR WHAT YOU ARE,
I GOTTA RESET MY FOCUS AND START
THIS WHOLE THING OVER AGAIN.
I WON'T GET DITCHED
BY ANOTHER THIRTEEN B.
ALL RIGHT, BABY.
YOU'RE MY THIRTEEN B TURBO.
LET'S TEAR THIS ROAD UP!
- OKAY, THANKS A LOT.
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE THIS.
BUT THEY'RE ACTUALLY PACING
EACH OTHER, FROM WHAT HE SAID.
- IT'S BEEN COMMON KNOWLEDGE
FOR A LONG TIME,
SINCE THE ENGINE WAS DESIGNED,
THAT A SINGLE TURBINE
TURBO IS GOING TO LAG.
BUT THE TURBINES THESE DAYS
ARE SO WELL DESIGNED
THAT IT STILL SPOOLS
EVEN AT A VERY LOW
AMOUNT OF PRESSURE.
THAT KIND OF POWER
WORKS WELL IN THIS COURSE,
MAKING HER FD
THE EASIER TWO TO DRIVE.
THE MOTOR MUST'VE BEEN
TUNED BY SOMEONE
WITH A WEALTH OF KNOWLEDGE
ABOUT THIS COURSE.
COMPARED TO THAT, KEISUKE'S
CAR IS A TWIN TURBO.
IT'S POWER OUTPUT DOESN'T MATCH
THIS COURSE AS WELL AS HERS.
THAT'S LIKE A HANDICAP
FOR KEISUKE, WHICH IS WHY,
AT LEAST FOR THE MOMENT,
THE RACE IS TIED.
- WAIT A MINUTE, IF YOU KNEW
THAT MUCH ALREADY,
COULDN'T WE HAVE ADDRESSED
IT DURING THE EARLY RUNS
AND TWEAKED THE CAR
TO COMPENSATE FOR IT?
THAT COULD'VE HELPED HIM.
- NO WAY. RELYING ON SETTINGS
TO CONTROL THE POWER
OF YOUR VEHICLE SHOWS WEAKNESS.
IT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH
FOR D'S DRIVERS. PERIOD.
KEEP IN MIND WE'RE WORKING
ON ACCELERATION TECHNIQUE
IN THIS RACE.
WITH A COURSE LIKE THIS ONE,
WHERE THE SURFACE IS IN
TERRIBLE CONDITION
GETTING TRACTION IS
HORRIBLY DIFFICULT,
WHICH MAKES THIS THE PERFECT
SETTING FOR OUR PURPOSES.
MAKING THE ASSUMPTION
THAT KEISUKE IS CAPABLE
OF CONTROLLING HIS ACCELERATOR
ON FIVE DIFFERENT LEVELS.
THIS KIND OF TRAINING
IS WHAT HE NEEDS
TO INCREASE THAT NUMBER TO TEN.
- TEN LEVELS?
- I'VE PRACTICED PLENTY
OF THINGS LIKE THAT MYSELF.
- ON THE STRAIGHAWAYS
SHE OPENS UP THE GAP A BIT.
COULD HER CAR BE MORE
POWERFUL THAN MINE?
BUT IF SO, HOW DOES
IT GET MORE STABILITY
COMING OUT OF A
CORNER THAN I DO?
I DON'T GET IT, I'M STILL
HAVING MORE TROUBLE
OPENING UP THE ACCELERATOR.
AM I THAT BAD OF A DRIVER?
I DON'T GET ANY OF THIS, BRO.
YOU TOLD ME THAT HER CAR'S
A SINGLE TURBINE,
BUT SO WHAT? WHAT THE HELL
DOES THAT MATTER?
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
A SINGLE AND A TWIN TURBINE?
- ( tires screeching )
- EVEN WHEN WE GUN IT
AT THE SAME POINT,
HER CAR GLIDES ALONG WHILE
MINE SLIDES LIKE IT'S ON ICE.
EVERYTHING I TRY JUST PUTS
MORE STRESS ON MY TIRES.
SO WHAT DO I DO?
DELAY THE TIMING OF OPENING UP
THE ACCELERATOR?
NO WAY. I DO THAT,
SHE JUST GETS FARTHER AHEAD.
I GOTTA CHANGE THE WAY
I PUT MY FOOT DOWN.
I GOTTA BE MORE DELICATE.
STEP DOWN LIKE A CENTIMETER,
WHEN I'M USUALLY
STEPPING DOWN TWO.
WAIT A BREATH, THEN STEP DOWN
ANOTHER CENTIMETER.
I'M STILL STEPPING DOWN
TOO HARD! DAMMIT!
THIS IS TOUGHER THAN I THOUGHT!
I'VE NEVER TRIED A DELICATE
ACCELERATION TECHNIQUE BEFORE.
THIS IS KILLING ME!
- ( engine revving )
♪ DAMN YOU, WHAT DO YOU MEAN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU DROWN ME ♪
- IT'S ELECTRIFYING!
I CAN FEEL HIS EYES ON ME,
BURNING THOUGH MY BACK.
WE'RE CONNECTED JUST LIKE I
KNEW WE'D BE. THE TWO OF US,
ALONE OUT HERE.
JUST ME AND MY DARLING.
I'VE NEVER HAD THIS
MUCH FUN BEFORE.
I DON'T WANT THIS TO END.
I WANT TO KEEP DRIVING
LIKE THIS FOREVER.
- THIS IS SO FREAKIN' WEIRD.
DIFFERENT FROM THE
BATTLES I USUALLY RUN.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE...
LIKE I'M COMFORTABLE.
BUT THE TENSION IS STILL
THROUGH THE ROOF.
- ( engine revving )
- THE GOAL'S RIGHT
IN FRONT OF US.
IF I KEEP UP MY SPEED I CAN
PULL THIS INTO A SECOND RUN.
- THERE IT IS! I GOTCHA, BRO.
THAT'S THE SINGLE
TURBINE'S WEAKNESS.
MAN, HOW COULD I HAVE
BEEN SO BLIND AND STUPID?
WHY DIDN'T I
REALIZE IT SOONER?
HER CAR'S FAST WHEN
IT'S RUNNING SMOOTH,
BUT DISRUPT IT'S RHYTHM
AND THAT SUCKER'S
WEAKNESS IS OBVIOUS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW RIGHT
I AM ABOUT THIS,
BUT I'M BETTING THAT
SINGLE TURBO'S GOTTA BE PEAKY.
- ( tires screeching )
- SHE LET OFF THE ACCELERATOR
AND HER BOOST PRESSURE FELL.
THIS IS IT! HERE'S WHERE
MY TWIN TURBO
AND IT'S MISSING LAG SHOWS
IT'S REAL WORTH!
- NO. PLEASE DON'T PASS ME.
I WANT TO KEEP DRIVING.
I DON'T WANT THIS TO END.
PLEASE, DARLING, DON'T GO!
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ WHO YOU WANNA BE,
WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA SEE,
WHAT YOU WANNA SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪