- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ DOGFIGHT ♪
♪ DOG FIGHT ♪
- ♪ YOU'RE BIG TIME GAMBLER ♪
- ♪ BREAK IT, BREAK IT
STRIKE IT, SHAKE IT ♪
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I PULLED THAT OFF.
IT WAS A BEAST BUT I WON IT.
RIGHT WHEN WE PULLED OFF
THE START,
I NOTICED I HAD
THE CAR SET WRONG.
SCREWED ME UP AT FIRST,
BUT I GOT HER BACK.
EVENTUALLY,
I SWITCHED TECHNIQUES,
ACCELERATING DIFFERENTLY
TO SAVE MY TIRES.
- STILL, IT'S A HELL OF A THING
BEING ABLE TO CATCH ON
TO YOUR OPPONENT'S WEAKNESS
IN THE THICK OF EVERYTHING.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I'M SURPRISED I NAILED IT. BUT I
NOTICED SOMETHING.
HER CAR WOBBLED FOR A SECOND.
SHE REGAINED CONTROL RIGHT AWAY,
BUT LOST SPEED SO FAST
I ALMOST SLAMMED INTO HER.
THAT'S WHEN IT HIT ME.
SUCKER'S GOTTA BE PEAKY, RIGHT?
MASSIVE TURBO LAG.
THERE'S NO OTHER REASON IT'D
SLIDE AROUND LIKE THAT.
IT'S A BAD ASS PIECE OF HARDWARE
IN A STRAIGHTFORWARD BATTLE,
BUT WEAKER IN HELL
IN A DOGFIGHT.
IF I'D PUT THAT
TOGETHER EARLIER ON,
I WOULD'VE TAKEN SOME OF
THE HEAT OFF MYSELF
AND RELAXED A LITTLE.
- DON'T FORGET THE ACCELERATION
TECHNIQUES YOU'VE LEARNED.
I'M SERIOUS.
WHEN WE'RE BACK IN AKAGI,
I WANT YOU TO PRACTICE
THEM EVERYDAY
UNTIL THEY'RE INSTINCTIVE.
THEY MIGHT SEEM SIMPLE, BUT
THESE TECHNIQUES AREN'T EASY.
AND WHEN YOU MASTER THEM, YOUR
ABILITY TO MANAGE YOUR TIRES
SHOULD GET A LOT BETTER.
- I HEAR YOU.
YOU HAD THIS THING PLANNED
ALL ALONG DIDN'T YOU, MAN?
- I'M SORRY, GUYS.
- YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO APOLOGIZE
FOR AS LONG AS YOU
DID YOUR BEST.
- AND YOU DID, RIGHT?
- MMM-HMM.
- WELL? THEN THERE'S NO SHAME
IN LOSING TO SOMEONE
WHO WAS JUST A LITTLE BETTER.
I THOUGHT THE GUY'D RUSH
AND BURN OUT HIS TIRES.
NEVER THOUGHT HE'D ADAPT
TO THE CHANGES ON THE ROAD.
BUT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE MESS
HE CHANGED HIS WHOLE APPROACH
TO THE BATTLE.
I KNOW THEY'RE OUR ENEMIES,
BUT I'M STILL IMPRESSED.
RIGHT, WE ALL KNOW
THE DOWNHILL'S NEXT.
I'M GOING TO PULL EVERY TRICK
I GOT OUT OF MY SLEEVE
TO WIN THIS ONE.
- WE FOUND OUT THE ORDER.
- YEAH, I'M GONNA BE LEADING.
I ALREADY HEARD.
- YEAH, IT'S KINDA WEIRD,
BUT WHEN I WAS TALKING
TO THEM OVER THERE
THEY WERE VERY SPECIFIC
ON WANTING TO CHASE.
HOW'S IT LOOK?
- SWEET. SHE'S READY TO
CRANK UP WHENEVER.
- COOL. I'LL TELL THEM
WE'RE READY.
LET'S GET THE CARS OVER
TO THE STARTING LINE!
- ( engine starting )
- HEY, WHATEVER GOES DOWN,
JUST STAY COOL OUT THERE, OKAY?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME.
I KNOW THERE'S NO CHANCE
I'LL KEEP UP.
BUT I NEED TO SEE HOW
THIS EIGHT-SIX DRIVES
FOR AS LONG AS I CAN.
AND NOT JUST FOR ME.
I AM CURIOUS, BUT I NEED TO
GET THE INFO SO I CAN USE IT
IN THE SECOND ROUND
OF THE SAITAMA SHOWDOWN.
MY FELLAS NEED THE HELP.
- FUJIWARA.
- YEAH?
- DON'T DITCH THE GUY
FOLLOWING YOU.
I WANT HIM TO KEEP UP
FOR A WHILE, OKAY?
IF HE STARTS TO FALL
A LITTLE BEHIND,
SLOW DOWN AND LET HIM CATCH UP.
BUT THE SECOND THAT FIRST
HAIRPIN'S IN YOUR REAR VIEW,
LEAVE HIM SUCKING YOUR EXHAUST.
AFTER THAT, JUST FLOOR IT
UNTIL YOU MAKE THROUGH
THE FINISH LINE.
ARE WE CLEAR? ONLY LEAD HIM
THROUGH THAT FIRST HAIRPIN.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- FUMIHIRO, LIGHT THEM UP.
- RIGHT ON.
ALL RIGHT, HERE COMES
THE COUNTDOWN!
STARTING IN FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE, GO!
- ( tires screeching )
- SURPRISED YOU MADE
IT OUT, WATARU.
- WELL, PROJECT D'S TWIN ACES
ARE HERE IN SAITAMA,
WHAT DO YOU THINK I'M GONNA DO?
SIT ON MY THUMBS WAITING
TO HEAR HOW IT WENT?
- THE DOWNHILL MUST'VE
STARTED ALREADY.
- YEAH, IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME.
- NOW THAT YOUR RUN'S FINISHED,
I'VE CALMED DOWN ENOUGH
TO REALIZE I'M STARVING.
- WE HAVE ANYTHING?
- CHECK IN VAN ONE.
I THINK THERE'S STILL SOME
RICE BALLS LEFT OVER
FROM THE STORE WE HIT
ON THE WAY HERE.
- EXCELLENT. I'M GONNA GO
THROW SOME OF THOSE DOWN.
WANT ME TO BRING
YOU BACK A COUPLE?
- NAH, I'M COOL.
- ALL RIGHT.
- KEISUKE?
I JUST WANTED TO SAY, THANK
YOU FOR EVERYTHING YOU DID.
- WHAT? I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
AT LEAST, NOT ANYTHING
THAT'D MAKE YOU TO BOW TO ME.
- BUT OF COURSE YOU DID.
YOU FIXED MY FD WHEN I
WAS STUCK ALONE.
- OH, THAT? COME ON,
YOU GOTTA LET THAT GO.
THAT WAS ALL BEFORE THE RACE.
IT'S ANCIENT HISTORY, OKAY?
- BUT, IT WAS...
- LOOK, I SHOULD PROBABLY
SAY THANKS TO YOU, TOO.
I LEARNED A LOT
DRIVING WITH YOU TONIGHT.
IT WAS A MONSTER BATTLE. REALLY.
YOU GOT SKILLS AND YOU CAN FLY
OUT THERE WHEN YOU NEED TO.
I'M NOT BLOWING SMOKE
UP YOUR ASS.
ANYBODY'LL TELL YOU
I'M NOT LIKE THAT.
WHEN WE WERE GEARING UP,
I THINK I MIGHT HAVE COME
DOWN TOO HARD ON YOU.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- NO. NO, IT'S OKAY.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE JUST FORGET THE WHOLE THING,
CALL IT EVEN.
- SURE, I UH...
IT'S JUST, I HAD SO MUCH FUN
RACING WITH YOU TONIGHT.
IS IT CRAZY THAT THIS IS ONE OF
THE BEST TIMES I'VE EVER HAD?
- ( tires screeching )
- I DON'T KNOW IF HIS
CORNERING IS AMAZING
OR THE CRAZIEST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN.
- ( stuttering ) SO,
I WAS THINKING THAT...
I WAS WONDERING IF MAYBE BY ANY
CHANCE YOU WERE DATING SOMEBODY?
- WHAT, LIKE A GIRLFRIEND,
YOU MEAN? YEAH, NOT REALLY.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR CHICKS,
NOT WHEN I'M DRIVING.
- I GOT TIME TRIALS, NEW...
- OKAY! SEE YOU LATER!
- WHOA, WAIT!
WHAT A WEIRD CHICK.
SHE'S GOT ISSUES.
- AWKWARD.
- ♪ POWER OF SOUND ♪
♪ POWER OF YOUR FEELINGS ♪
- IT'S ALMOST LIKE
THERE'S A FLOW BEHIND HIM.
I CAN'T GET SUCKED INTO IT.
BUT WHY CAN'T I KEEP UP?
I DIDN'T EXPECT THAT.
MAYBE 'CAUSE THE SLOPE
IN THIS FIRST SECTION
ISN'T AS STEEP
AS THE REST OF THE COURSE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER REASON.
HE'S BETTER THAN THAT.
MY HEART'S SLAMMING
AGAINST MY RIBS.
IT FEELS LIKE I'M OUT HERE FOR
THE FIRST DRIVE IN A NEW CAR.
I'M GOING TO BURN EVERY
SINGLE DETAIL OF THIS RACE
INTO MY MEMORY.
NOW, COME ON.
SHOW ME THIS UNREAL TECHNIQUE
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT!
- Ryosuke: DON'T DITCH THE GUY
FOLLOWING YOU.
I WANT HIM TO KEEP UP
FOR AWHILE, OKAY?
IF HE STARTS TO FALL
A LITTLE BEHIND,
SLOW DOWN AND LET HIM CATCH UP.
BUT THE SECOND THAT FIRST
HAIRPIN'S IN YOUR REARVIEW,
LEAVE HIM SUCKING YOUR EXHAUST.
ARE WE CLEAR? ONLY LEAD HIM
THROUGH THAT FIRST HAIRPIN.
- ♪ POWER OF SOUND ♪
♪ POWER, MAKE ME DIZZY ♪
♪ ENTER MY MIND
AND TAKE ME NOW ♪
♪ I WILL CRASH INTO THE MUSIC ♪
♪ POWER OF SOUND ♪
- Wataru: SO NOBUHIKO, WHAT'D
YOU THINK OF THE RUN?
GOING UP AGAINST THE FASTEST
DOWNHILLER FROM GUNMA.
MUST'VE BEEN PRETTY HOT
UP IN THERE.
- YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT RACING HIM WAS LIKE?
THE WHOLE DAMN THING ENDED
AFTER THE FIRST HAIRPIN TURN.
- WHEN I TOOK ON THAT EIGHT-SIX,
THE BATTLE WAS SO NECK-AND-NECK
THE WHOLE TIME
THAT EITHER ONE OF US
COULD HAVE PULLED OUT THE WIN,
WE DID HAVE TO TAKE IT
INTO A FIFTH RUN AND EVERYTHING,
I MEAN I'M JUST SAYING.
- YOU KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE YOUR BURN WAS A COMBO
OF UPHILL AND DOWNHILL.
IF YOU'D RACED HIM
ON A STRICTLY DOWNHILL RUN,
I DOUBT YOU COULD'VE
LASTED THAT LONG.
- ( scoffs ) GOT ANY OTHER
SCABS YOU WANNA PICK AT?
STILL, YOU GOT A POINT.
HIS DOWNHILL FIGHT'S MEAN.
- YEAH, BUT, THERE'S STILL
ONE THING THAT'S BUGGING ME
ABOUT THAT RUN.
WHEN WE WERE OUT THERE,
I GOT THE DISTINCT FEELING
HE WAS LETTING ME
KEEP UP ON PURPOSE.
- HMM?
THAT'S STUPID. WHY WOULD HE?
- IF I KNEW, I'D TELL YOU.
MAYBE I'M PUTTING TOO MUCH
THOUGHT INTO THIS.
EITHER WAY, I DIDN'T
GET TO WATCH HIM
FOR AS LONG AS I'D HAVE LIKED,
BUT I DID SEE
SOMETHING INTERESTING.
AND I KNOW HOW TO BEAT HIM.
- Man: SERIOUSLY?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY.
- THIS IS THE TIME TRIAL, RIGHT?
DUDE'S FAST.
GOT SOME FIRE IN THERE.
- I WONDER WHAT KIND OF RECORD
HE'S GONNA LEAVE US
WHEN HE'S DONE WITH OUR COURSE.
STILL, WHATEVER HE DOES, TODAY'S
SHOW WAS JUST A PROLOGUE
TO ROUND TWO
OF THE SAITAMA SHOWDOWN.
THESE GUYS ARE
WORTHY OPPONENTS.
I GUARANTEE YOU,
WE'RE GONNA DEFEAT PROJECT D!
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
- WHAT'S UP, MAN?
- YO!
- KENJI. SO, I DON'T GUESS YOU
HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT LANGUAGE
THE GREETING "YO"
COMES FROM, DO YOU?
- SHUT UP, MAN. I BROUGHT YOU
SOMETHING. IT'S D'S HOMEPAGE.
- COOL! WELL, HAND IT OVER!
- ( exclaiming ) ME FIRST!
ME FIRST! I WANNA SEE IT!
- Kenji: THEY'RE STILL
DOMINATING. NOTHING NEW.
WON BOTH THE UPHILL AND DOWNHILL
WITH BIG LEADS ON BOTH.
SET COURSE RECORDS, TOO.
YOU KNOW, THE USUAL.
- ( laughing )
THEY'RE SO BADASS.
ALWAYS LAYING TRACKS ON ROADS
THEY'VE NEVER DRIVEN,
AND THEY ALWAYS WIN.
- THOSE GUYS SURE ARE
INCREDIBLE, ALL RIGHT.
I'D KILL TO GO CHECKOUT A RACE
OF THEIRS SOMEDAY.
- YOU AND ME BOTH. YOU KNOW,
SAITAMA'S NOT THAT FAR AWAY.
SO HOW ABOUT THIS, NEXT
BATTLE, WE ALL GO CHECK IT OUT.
- I'M DOWN FOR IT,
IF YOU GUYS ARE.
- I'M IN! LET'S FREAKING
DO IT! YEAH!
- Girl: THE FACT THAT YOU TALKED
TO THE GUY AT ALL IS IMPRESSIVE.
AND YOU ASKED HIM IF HE'S GOT
A GIRLFRIEND, THAT'S UNREAL.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
I WAS REALLY PROUD OF MYSELF.
- YOU SCORED BIG TIME, HITTING
ON A SINGLE GUY. WELL DONE.
I BET HE'S KICKING BACK
RIGHT NOW,
THINKING ABOUT THAT HOTTIE
THAT THOUGHT HE WAS CUTE.
- DO YOU THINK SO?
- SURE, WHY WOULDN'T HE BE?
AS LONG AS HE'S NOT
BLIND, DEAF, AND STUPID
HE'D HAVE TO HAVE KNOWN
YOU WERE INTO HIM.
ANY MAN WITH A PULSE
WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO STOP
ROLLING THAT OVER
IN HIS TINY BRAIN.
- I'M LOSING MY MIND OVER THIS!
MY DARLING IS THINKING
ABOUT ME RIGHT NOW!
- WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
- CHILL OUT.
- OKAY, LOOK,
I NEED TO GET PRETTY, FAST.
I'VE NEVER FELT
LIKE THIS BEFORE,
AND I DON'T WANT TO BLOW IT
'CAUSE I LOOK LIKE A BOY.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO
IGNORE ME, YOU KNOW?
- ( tires screeching )
- KEISUKE'S GOT A GOOD REP
WITH THE CHICKS RIGHT?
- WHERE THE HELL
DID THAT COME FROM?
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR A DATE?
I DON'T KNOW. JUST THOUGHT
HE'S KINDA GOT THAT VIBE
GOING ON, I GUESS.
( chuckling )
- EVERYBODY LIKES KEISUKE.
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
ESPECIALLY THE CHICKS.
- YEAH, COOL.
- BUT LIKE THEM OR NOT,
HE HASN'T HAD ENOUGH TIME
TO DATE ANYONE IN A FEW YEARS.
-  WHOA! A FEW YEARS?
- I GUESS HE FIGURES
THEY'RE TOO MUCH TROUBLE.
LAST GIRL HE WAS WITH
THEY GOT ALONG PRETTY WELL.
THEY DATED FOR A WHILE, BUT
THEN THE TWO OF THEM SPLIT UP
WHEN HE BOUGHT HIS FD AND
JOINED WITH THE RED SUNS.
KEISUKE IS THE KINDA GUY WHO
DOESN'T LIKE TO DO ANYTHING
UNLESS HE CAN DO IT ALL THE WAY.
HE CAN'T SPLIT HIS CONCENTRATION
LIKE HIS BROTHER CAN.
IT'S NOT ON HIS
LIST OF STRENGTHS.
HE DUMPED HER, SAYING HE WAS
TOO BUSY TO MAKE TIME FOR HER.
AND HE STARTED SLAUGHTERING
THE MOUNTAIN PASS
EVERY SINGLE NIGHT.
EVERYONE'S GOT THEIR
OWN WAY OF COPING, I GUESS.
- HELLO.
- I RECOGNIZE THAT FD.
- CRAP! THERE SHE IS!
- HEY.
- All: HI.
- Tomiguchi: DUDE, YOU THINK
SHE CAME HERE TO SEE KEISUKE?
- Fumihiro: PROBABLY.
- Kenta: THERE'S NO
PROBABLY ABOUT IT!
WHAT ELSE WOULD SHE
BE HERE FOR?
- ( car approaching )
- DUDE, CHECK IT OUT,
HE'S BACK.
- Keisuke: YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
- Kyoko: I HEARD THIS WAS
YOUR HOME COURSE, SO YEAH.
YOU DRIVE EVERY NIGHT,
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE NOT RACING?
- NA. I WOULDN'T SAY
EVERY NIGHT.
BUT I GOTTA WORK ON PERFECTING
MY ACCELERATOR TECHNIQUES,
SO I TRY TO COME OUT HERE
AND GET A COUPLE RUNS IN
EVERY TIME I GET A CHANCE.
- YOU'RE SO GOOD I'M SURPRISED
YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO WORK ON.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
REMINDS ME THAT YOU AND I
ARE ON VERY DIFFERENT LEVELS
AS RACERS.
- SO, WHY'D YOU COME
OUT HERE TONIGHT?
- I WAS HOPING
I'D BE ABLE TO SEE YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE YOU.
I'M NOT BUGGING YOU, AM I?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
- SHUT UP.
- LOOK, KYOKO, LET ME BE
STRAIGHT UP WITH YOU.
IF THAT'S THE ONLY REASON YOU'RE
COMING OUT HERE, THEN DON'T.
- BUT WHY NOT? I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU LIKED ME. AM I WRONG?
- THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH ME LIKING YOU OR NOT.
- THEN WHAT IS IT?
- YOU BEING HERE
JUST DOESN'T WORK FOR ME.
- WAIT! LISTEN TO ME.
FOR A SECOND.
I WON'T BLOW YOUR
CONCENTRATION.
ISN'T IT OKAY IF I JUST WATCH
YOU DRIVE? THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I WANT TO SEE YOU
BEHIND THE WHEEL AGAIN.
I'LL STAY OUT OF
YOUR WAY. COOL?
JUST DON'T HATE ME.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN TAKE IT.
IT MIGHT SOUND DUMB, BUT I'VE
NEVER FELT LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO,
SO HERE I AM.
I LIKE YOU. I DO.
IT'S JUST THAT SIMPLE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
THIS INTO A GUY BEFORE.
I MEAN, I'VE LIKED OTHER GUYS,
SURE, BUT THIS FEELS DIFFERENT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO SAY IT.
THIS MIGHT BE ONE SIDED, BUT,
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
I WANT TO KEEP SEEING YOU.
IF IT'S HERE, OR OUT,
OR WHEREVER, I DON'T CARE.
THAT'S WHY I CAME,
TO TELL YOU THAT.
SO IS IT COOL BY YOU IF I COME
BACK OUT SOME OTHER TIME?
I'D REALLY, REALLY LIKE TO.
- YOU DON'T GET IT.
I TOLD YOU
I DIDN'T WANT YOU HERE,
BUT HERE YOU ARE
PUSHING YOURSELF ON ME.
IF I REALLY HATED YOU,
LIKE YOU SAID,
I'D JUST IGNORE
YOU AND WALK OFF.
BUT I CAN'T DO THAT, WHICH IS
WHY YOU'LL ONLY GET IN MY WAY.
- ( sniffling )
- IS IT SINKING IN? YOU'LL SCREW
ME UP IF YOU HANG AROUND HERE.
SO THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
I DON'T WANNA SEE YOU
HERE ANYMORE.
- ARE YOU COOL
WITH THIS, KEISUKE?
- WHAT THE HELL ELSE CAN I DO?
NOW MY FOCUS IS ALL OFF.
I'M OUT, GUYS.
NO DRIVING FOR ME TONIGHT.
- CALL YOU TOMORROW.
- YEAH.
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE I'M RUSHING THINGS ON THIS
ACCELERATION TRAINING.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE TIME
TO RELAX THESE DAYS.
BUT I LET UP FOR ONE SECOND,
AND TAKUMI'S GOING TO
LEAVE ME IN HIS WAKE.
HE KEEPS GETTING
BETTER AND BETTER
SINCE HE JOINED UP WITH D.
IT'S KILLING ME.
I CAN'T WASTE ANY OF MY TIME
SLUSHING AROUND
WITH SOME STUPID CHICK.
'CAUSE HE'S OUT THERE
DRIVING EVERY DAY TOO.
- IS IT SINKING IN? YOU'LL SCREW
ME UP IF YOU HANG AROUND.
SO THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
I DON'T WANNA SEE YOU
HERE ANYMORE.
- IF I THINK ABOUT IT FROM HIS
POINT OF VIEW, I GET IT.
HIS DRIVING'S
IMPORTANT TO HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M SUPPOSED TO DO NOW.
I'VE NEVER LIKED A GUY
THIS MUCH, EVER.
I WANNA GO TO HIM, BUT I DON'T
WANT TO PUSH HIM AWAY.
STILL, IT'S JUST ONE PROBLEM.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO
LET ONE LITTLE THING
SHUT DOWN HOW I'M FEELING.
I CAN'T GIVE UP ON THIS.
- Nobuhiko: I'M LOOKING
FOR SOMEBODY?
- HEY, NOBUHIKO. OVER HERE.
- NEVER MIND.
THAT'S THE GUY OVER THERE.
- YOU'RE LATE, PAL.
- SORRY,
TRAFFIC WAS A NIGHTMARE.
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU TWO.
THIS IS MY COUSIN, NOBUHIKO.
- SWEET DRIVER
BUT HE'S ALWAYS LATE.
- HOW YOU DOING?
- SO, THIS IS SAKAMOTO,
THE GUY WE TALKED ABOUT.
- WHAT'S UP?
- THIS DUDE'LL BLOW YOUR
DOORS OFF. HE'S FAST.
I MEAN, WE ALL KNOW THAT
RALLY DRIVERS ARE FREAKING NUTS
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
SO NO ONE IS BETTER SUITED FOR
THE RACE YOU'RE ABOUT TO RUN
THAN THIS GUY.
- IF WATARU RECOMMENDS YOU,
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR
ME. SHOULD BE FINE.
- YOU SAID YOU HAD SOME GOOD
NEWS FOR US. LET'S HEAR IT.
I WANT TO KNOW ALL ABOUT
THIS PLAN YOU'VE GOT
TO BEAT OUR BUDDY
IN THE EIGHT-SIX.
- SURE. I ANALYZED THE DATA
ON D'S PREVIOUS BATTLES.
THEN I FACTORED IN WHAT I
SAW WITH MY OWN TWO EYES.
I WAS BEHIND THAT EIGHT-SIX LONG
ENOUGH TO LEARN A FEW THINGS.
USING SIMPLE DEDUCTION AND
PROCESS OF ELIMINATION,
I FOUND SOMETHING.
- HEY, WHY DON'T YOU
USE SMALLER WORDS
AND START TALKING TO US LIKE
REGULAR PEOPLE.
NEITHER OF US GOT
THE BOOK SMARTS YOU DO.
WE'RE A LITTLE MORE ON THE
STREET SMART SIDE OF THINGS.
- YEAH, EASE UP. HE'S RETARDED.
- BUT WHAT I'M SAYING IS
ACTUALLY REALLY EASY TO GRASP.
HEY, SAKAMOTO, HAVE YOU
EVER DRIVEN AN FR BEFORE?
- DUDE...
- SAKAMOTO HERE CAN DRIVE
ANYTHING YOU GIVE HIM,
AND FRS ARE WHAT HE'S MOST
EXPERIENCED WITH.
HE'S REALLY AWESOME, MAN.
- THEN THAT'LL WORK.
I'VE BROUGHT THE ULTIMATE
WEAPON WITH ME,
IF YOU GUYS WANNA CHECK IT OUT.
- WHAT? ULTIMATE WEAPON?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WHOA. FOR REAL,
THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE CALLING THE
ULTIMATE WEAPON?
YOU'RE NOT SCREWING WITH ME
OR SOMETHING, ARE YOU MAN?
I MEAN, DUDE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
- (singing in Japanese )
♪ WHO YOU WANNA BE,
WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA SEE,
WHAT YOU WANNA SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
♪ BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
♪ STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪