- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese)
♪ DOGFIGHT ♪
- ♪ BACKFIRE ♪
- ♪ DOGFIGHT ♪
- ♪ YOU'RE BIG TIME GAMBLER ♪
- ♪ BREAK IT, BREAK IT
STRIKE IT, SHAKE IT ♪
♪ BABY, THIS IS YOUR ECSTASY ♪
- Tohru: FINALLY,
THEIR PAGE IS UP!
CHECK IT OUT. PROJECT D.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY WON AGAIN.
- Atsuro: THAT'S A
COURSE RECORD.
- Tohru: AMAZING. THEY'VE
WON EVERY MATCH
ON EVERY OPPONENT'S
TURF THEY'VE HIT.
- Nao: SO, WHAT'S A PROJECT D?
- Atsuro: YA KNOW REE-YO-SKAY
TAKAHASHI, RIGHT?
- Nao: I'M NOT BLIND.
THAT SUPER HOT GUY?
- NYWAY, HE PUT TOGETHER THIS
SPECIAL TEAM TO COMPETE WITH
OTHER TEAMS OUTSIDE
HIS PREFECTURE.
- Tohru: HE USES HIS COMPUTER
TO LURE IN THE CHALLENGERS,
THEN HE POSTS THE RESULTS
ON HIS WEB PAGE.
HE PUTS THE OPPONENT'S
NAMES UP THERE.
HELL, EVEN THE ROAD NAMES GO UP.
SO, ARE THEY COMING OUT OR NOT?
- FROM WHAT I'VE HEARD, I THINK
WE'LL PROBABLY SEE THEM SOON.
THEY WERE LAST SEEN ON OSAGIRI
HIGHWAY NOT TOO LONG AGO.
- WELL IT'S ABOUT TIME.
GUESS I'LL GO AHEAD
AND DO THE DOWNHILL.
THE UPHILL'S ALL YOURS.
YOUR THIRTY-FOUR WILL
HANDLE IT BETTER.
- Atsuro: YEAH. THAT'S WHAT
I WAS THINKIN' TOO.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW FIERCE THE
COMPETITION IS OVER IN GUNMA.
BUT I WANNA SHOW THESE GUYS
WE'LL REDEFINE THE TERM "GETTING
BURNED" IF THEY MESS WITH US.
- Nao: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
NOT MORE NEW TIRES.
DIDN'T YOU JUST BUY NEW ONES
A COUPLE UH WEEKS AGO?
- YEAH, BUT THOSE WERE JUST
CHEAP LITTLE PLACE HOLDERS.
THEIR GRIP STINKS
OUTSIDE OF THE CITY.
I'M GONNA NEED TO
GET A NEW SET.
THAT'S HOW I'LL WIN THOSE
TIME ATTACKS. I KNOW IT.
NAO, PLEASE.
YOU GOTTA HELP ME.
WHEN I GET MY SUMMER BONUS
I'LL PAY YOU BACK, I PROMISE.
- YOU'VE ALWAYS SPENT TOO MUCH
MONEY ON YOUR STUPID CAR.
- HUH?
- IT WOULD JUST BE NICE IF YOU
PUT SOME OF YOUR MONEY AWAY
WITH OUR FUTURE IN MIND.
SIX YEARS! TOHRU, HOW LONG
DO YOU EXPECT US TO DO THIS?
THE WAY THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING,
I DON'T SEE US EVER
GETTING MARRIED.
- GREAT.
MY FAVORITE TOPIC AGAIN.
DO YOU KNOW HOW SICK I AM
OF HEARING ABOUT THIS?
- DO YOU KNOW HOW SICK I AM
OF BRINGING IT UP
'CAUSE YOU NEVER LISTEN?
OK. IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
I'LL LEND YOU THE MONEY.
- YEAH? YOU WILL?
YOU'RE A LIFE SAVER, BABE!
- BUT THERE'S ONE CONDITION.
- YEAH, WHAT KIND?
- THE KIND THAT SAYS
YOU QUIT RACING ALL TOGETHER,
IF YOU LOSE THIS NEXT BATTLE.
- BUT YOU CAN'T MEAN THAT.
- I'M SERIOUS THIS TIME,
SO YOU BETTER HEAR ME.
I MEAN IT.
BREAK THIS PROMISE AND
I'LL LEAVE YOU FOR GOOD.
YOU'LL NEVER SEE ME AGAIN.
- ( car revving )
- THESE NEW TIRES FEEL GREAT.
JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
THIS BATTLE IS MINE. I MEAN,
NAO IS IMPORTANT TO ME, BUT...
THERE'S JUST NO WAY
I'M EVER QUITTING RACING!
- ( tires screeching )
- TOHRU, THEY'RE HERE!
- PROJECT D.
FINALLY, YOU SHOW YOURSELF.
- THAT'S AN FD.
WHAT'S THAT? AN EIGHT-SIX?
- WHOA. THESE GUYS REALLY KNOW
HOW TO MAKE AN ENTRANCE.
THEY MIGHT BE TOUGH.
- HEY, RYOSUKE, GET UP. WE'RE
HERE. COME ON IT'S TIME.
RYOSUKE!
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT HE'S DOING.
HIS CONCENTRATION IS
ALWAYS AMAZING.
WISH I COULD DO THAT.
HE HASN'T WOKEN UP ONCE
SINCE WE LEFT TAKASAKI.
NOT EVEN FOR A DRINK
OR TO USE THE CAN.
- MY BROTHER
UNDERSTANDS EFFICIENCY.
HE'S GOT MANY TALENTS,
THAT'S JUST ONE.
- HEY, MATSUMOTO. SORRY, MAN,
COULD YOU SNAG ME A WATER?
- YEAH, SURE.
- LET'S BEGIN.
- HOW'S IT GOING?
WE'RE PROJECT D,
FROM THE GUNMA AREA.
- PEOPLE KNOW US AS
THE SEVEN STAR LEAF.
ON THIS MOUNTAIN,
WE'RE THE MAIN TEAM THAT RACES.
WE'RE THE ONES TO BEAT.
SO NATURALLY YOU GUYS'LL BE
DRIVING AGAINST US.
- THAT SOUNDS GOOD,
WE'RE ALL READY TO GO.
NOW, I'M SURE SOMEONE CONTACTED
YOU ABOUT THIS EARLIER,
BUT, WE'D LIKE TO
PRACTICE HERE TONIGHT,
IF IT'S ALRIGHT WITH YOU.
THAT WAY, WE CAN BE
FULLY RESTED
AND PREPPED FOR
TOMORROW NIGHT'S RACE.
- I HEAR YA.
I GOT NO PROBLEM WITH THAT.
IF MY EYES AREN'T LYING,
YOU GUYS ONLY BROUGHT AN FD
AND AN EIGHT-SIX WITH YOU.
ONLY TWO CARS TO START?
WE SPECIALIZE IN BATTLING
OPPONENTS FAR AWAY.
THIS IS THE RESULT OF THAT.
WE'VE GOTTEN MORE EFFICIENT.
THE EIGHT-SIX IS FOR DOWNHILL.
THE FD IS FOR UPHILL.
AND THESE TWO GUYS
ARE OUR DOUBLE ACES.
ALRIGHT, WE'LL GET STARTED THEN.
- THEY'RE A LOT MORE POLITE
THAN I EXPECTED THEY'D BE.
RACERS USUALLY AREN'T THE
FRIENDLIEST GUYS.
- ( air hissing )
- I THOUGHT IT WAS WEIRD THAT
THEY ONLY BROUGHT TWO CARS,
BUT WHAT'S WITH THE THREE VANS?
ARE THEY SUPPORT UNITS?
WHAT ARE THEY HIDING IN THERE?
- THE EIGHT-SIX'S FINAL SETTINGS
ARE LOCKED IN AND READY.
WITH THE CHANGES WE MADE THEY'RE
LOOKING SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- THIS ISN'T A NORMAL
RACING TEAM.
RACERS USUALLY RIDE TOGETHER.
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE TO ME.
I MEAN, THREE SUPPORT VANS FOR
TWO CARS, I DUNNO ABOUT THAT.
A TEAM'S A TEAM, BUT AM I
THE ONLY ONE HERE WHO THINKS
THESE GUYS LOOK MORE LIKE
PROFESSIONAL CIRCUIT RACERS?
- LOOK, THEY JUST DO THIS CRAP
TO TRY TO PSYCHE US OUT.
YOU CAN'T LET 'EM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THEY
CAN ACCOMPLISH
WITH ONE NIGHT OF PRACTICE?
WE'VE BEEN DOING THIS
FOR TWO YEARS.
THAT'S TWO YEARS MORE
THAN THEY HAVE.
I MEAN, COME ON,
WE MUST'VE DRIVEN THIS COURSE
LIKE A THOUSAND TIMES ALREADY.
THEY COULD HAVE TWENTY SUPPORT
UNITS OUT HERE. WHO CARES?
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
IT'S DRIVER VERSUS DRIVER.
AND I DON'T EXACTLY
PLAN ON LOSING,
'SPECIALLY TO ANY
ONE POINT SIX LITER!
THIS IS MY TURF.
NO CRAP EIGHT-SIX IS
GONNA TAKE ME DOWN.
- OKAY. I UNDERSTAND.
THIS'LL WORK.
GIVE FUJIWARA THE BASIC RUNDOWN,
HAVE HIM THINK ABOUT IT,
THEN TELL HIM TO GET WITH ME
IF HE HAS ANY IDEAS.
- RIGHT.
- I DON'T WANT TO GO INTO
TOO MUCH DETAIL RIGHT NOW.
BUT THIS IS IMPORTANT.
HE SHOULD START THINKING
ABOUT THINGS ON HIS OWN.
- SURE, I GOTCHA.
- ( machine whirring )
- HAVE YOU SEEN THAT VIDEO YET?
- YEAH, I'VE WATCHED IT
LIKE FORTY TIMES ALREADY.
- I'M ASSUMING THAT MEANS YOU'VE
MEMORIZED THE COURSE, THEN?
FOR YOUR FIRST FIVE RUNS, I ONLY
WANT YOU AT SEVENTY PERCENT.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
WATCHING THE VIDEO
AND ACTUALLY DRIVING
THE COURSE.
BUT, I HOPE YOU PUT THAT
TOGETHER ALREADY.
FIRST AND FOREMOST YOU GOTTA
ADJUST TO THAT DIFFERENCE.
- SURE.
- KEISUKE, YOU UNDERSTANDING
WHAT I'M SAYING TOO, RIGHT?
YOU BRING UP
YOUR PACE ONLY AFTER
YOU'VE GOTTEN USED
TO THE DIFFERENCE.
- YEAH. YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT A THING.
- OKAY. THEN, GO.
- ( car revving )
- I'M GOING TOO.
AS LONG AS MY TIRES ARE SOLID,
I'M READY TO GIVE
IT ALL I'VE GOT.
- ( tires screeching )
- Atsuro: YOU MAY BE
RIGHT, TOHRU.
WHAT COULD THEY ACCOMPLISH
IN JUST ONE NIGHT?
THAT'S THE FRAME OF MIND
WE HAVE TO PUT OURSELVES IN
IF WE'RE GONNA WIN THIS.
THE MOMENT YOUR WHEELS
CROSS ONTO THAT COURSE,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO CHANGE THE WAY
YOU'VE BEEN THINKING ENTIRELY.
THE ONLY THINGS YOU CAN
TRUST ON THE ASPHALT
ARE YOUR DRIVING TECHNIQUE,
AND THE CAR YOU'RE
HOLDING ONTO.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( yawning )
'KAY I'M HEADING OUT.
- MMM.
- THANK YOU FROM COMING IN!
- ( humming)
( laughing )
- YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY,
ITSUKI. WHY'S THAT?
- C'MON, WHY WOULDN'T I BE,
IKTANI? DID YOU ALREADY FORGET?
CUZ IT'S T-MINUS ONE DAY
TO FREAKIN' PAYDAY!
- OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR FIRST BIG CHECK.
FIRST ONE SINCE JOINING
THE RANKS OF THE FULL TIMERS.
- IT FEELS WAY DIFFERENT FROM
WHEN I WAS WORKING PART TIME,
LIKE I'VE MATURED OR SOMETHING.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE ACTUALLY
BECOME AN ADULT.
- SO, MR ADULT, WHERE'S YOUR
FIRST PAYCHECK GOING?
- I'VE ALREADY MADE UP MY MIND.
IT'S GOING INTO A TURBO FOR
MY SWEET ASS EIGHT-FIVE!
- NOT THAT PIECE OF JUNK?
- NOW, BLOWING BY CARS
LIKE YOUR S-THIRTEEN...
( whooping )
...WILL BE EASIER THAN
EATING CAKE ON MY BIRTHDAY!
I ALREADY GOT A LOAN ESTIMATE
AND THE DUDE SAYS
IT'S LOOKING GOOD!
- YEAH?
- EVERY DAY I'M CLOSER
TO LIVING MY DREAMS!
THE EIGHT-FIVE OF AKINA
WILL SOON BECOME A LEGENDARY CAR
AMONG THE RACERS OF THE WORLD!
- SO YOU SAY.
- ( Itsuki making
driving noises )
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO TACKLE
THOSE MOUNTAIN PASSES
LIKE TAKUMI DOES!
- ( chuckles )
- YEAH, SPEAKING OF TAKUMI,
I WONDER WHAT HE'S UP TO.
HAVEN'T HEARD FROM HIM
IN A WHILE.
- THERE'S SOMETHING THAT'S
BEEN ON MY MIND SINCE LAST YEAR.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
MY DREAM IN LIFE.
ALL WINTER LONG, IT WAS ON MY
MIND. IT'S ALL I THOUGHT ABOUT.
I FINALLY FIGURED IT OUT.
WHAT I WANT TO DO IS DRIVE.
I WANNA DRIVE FASTER THAN THE
NEXT GUY, FASTER THAN ANYONE.
SO, I'VE DECIDED TO BE A
PROFESSIONAL DRIVER.
- ( crying )
I WANT TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I DON'T CARE WHEN IT IS,
BUT SOMEDAY.
- Man: FUJIWARA?
YO, FUJIWARA. WAKE UP.
- OH, HEY.
- ALWAYS DAYDREAMING
LIKE A LITTLE GIRL.
ARE YOU DONE FOR THE DAY
OR AREN'T YOU?
- UH, YEAH.
I'M ON THE EARLY SHIFT.
- YOU GOT A HOT DATE?
- I DON'T... WELL, NOT REALLY.
- NOT REALLY? AND YOU'RE
SO YOUNG. SUCH A SHAME.
- Fumihiro: HOLY CRAP.
THESE GUTTERS ARE WIDE OPEN.
- RYOSUKE SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT IT TO ME.
BUT I DIDN'T EXPECT THEM
TO BE QUITE LIKE THIS.
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN,
BACK IN GUNMA, THEY USE PANELS.
USUALLY, THE GUTTERS ARE
COMPLETELY COVERED IN CONCRETE.
IT WAS SO DARK DURING THE
PRACTICE RUNS LAST NIGHT,
THEY DIDN'T STAND OUT.
BUT IF EVEN ONE OF
YOUR TIRES DIPS
INTO THESE GUTTERS
AT RACING SPEEDS,
YOUR UNDERCARRIAGE
WILL BE TOTALED.
- YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING,
WHEN RYOSUKE MENTIONED
THIS LAST NIGHT,
HE MUST HAVE BEEN
WARNING ME.
HE TOLD ME THAT, "HOW YOU
OVERCOME THESE GUTTERS
IN THE RACE WILL WIN
OR LOSE IT FOR YOU."
- HE CAN SAY WHAT HE WANTS,
BUT THE BEST WE CAN DO IS JUST
BE CAREFUL NOT TO FALL IN.
LOOK, WE'RE JUST GOING TO
HAVE TO TRUST HIM.
THERE'S A LOT RYOSUKE KNOWS,
AND WE DON'T ALWAYS
UNDERSTAND WHAT HE MEANS
UNTIL THE VERY LAST
HAND IS DEALT.
AND THEN,
IT ALWAYS ENDS THE SAME.
IT'S EXACTLY THE WAY
HE PREDICTS IT'LL BE.
YOU CAN COUNT ON IT.
- Tohru: THIS TIME I BORED OUT
THE SIXTEEN HUNDRED V-SIX
TO AN EIGHTEEN HUNDRED.
I PUT IN HIGH
COMPRESSION PISTONS
AND A LIGHTENED FLY WHEEL,
AND THAT WAY SHE'LL GET
HER RESPONSE TIME A LOT CLOSER
TO THE LEVEL WE NEED IT.
THEN, I PUT IN QUAD-VALVE
SPORTS FUEL INJECTORS.
SHE'S A REAL BAD GIRL.
- IF YOU COMBINE WHAT YOU
GOT UNDER THE HOOD
WITH YOUR DRIVING
TECHNIQUE, TOHRU,
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE THE
ULTIMATE DOWNHILL MACHINE.
I GOTTA ADMIT, I'M JEALOUS.
- WITH ALL OF THIS, THERE'S NO
WAY I CAN LOSE. NO WAY.
- ( car revving )
- SO TELL ME BUNTA,
YOU STILL MAKING TAKUMI DO ALL
OF THE TOFU DELIVERIES?
- YEAH, IT'S NOT LIKE THINGS
HAVE REALLY CHANGED MUCH.
- BUT THE KID'S ALSO WORKING
ANOTHER FULL TIME JOB
DURING THE DAY.
THAT'S A LITTLE MUCH.
- LOOK HE CAN HANDLE IT, BESIDES
I DON'T EVER HEAR HIM COMPLAIN.
AND HE'S ACTUALLY BEEN WORKING
HARDER THAN EVER BEFORE.
- WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
- THAT PROJECT D TEAM
HAS BEEN GOOD FOR HIM.
THINK IT'S GIVEN HIM
SOME REAL MOTIVATION.
- YEAH, THEY'RE UNDEFEATED.
AND APPARENTLY THEY'RE BREAKING
RECORDS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
- SURE. THEY'RE THE ONES
TO BEAT RIGHT NOW,
BUT SOME DAY
THEY WILL LOSE.
- Man 1: ABOUT TIME! I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR THIS RACE FOREVER!
- Man 2: I WONDER IF PROJECT D
IS AS AWESOME AS THEY SAY?
- Man 3: IT DOESN'T MATTER.
ANY WAY YOU LOOK AT IT,
THE DOWNHILL BELONGS
TO THE SEVEN STAR LEAF.
I MEAN, TOHRU LOSING TO
SOME SLICK OUTSIDER?
C'MON, GIVE ME A BREAK.
- Man 4: HIS OPPONENT'S
AN EIGHT-SIX RIGHT?
- Man 3: AN FD IS A
TOUGH OPPONENT,
BUT AN EIGHT-SIX IS JUST
FLAT OUT OLD.
- THE OTHER TEAM WANTS TO
DO THE DOWNHILL FIRST.
I FIGURE THAT WORKS FINE FOR US.
AND IT'S NOT GONNA BE A
SIDE-BY-SIDE START.
IT'LL START WITH A CHASE,
ONE CAR CHASING THE OTHER.
THEY'LL GO FIRST.
NOW, I'M SURE YOU KNOW THIS.
BUT IF HE PULLS AWAY FROM YOU,
WE LOSE THE RACE.
TRY NOT TO FORGET THAT
WHEN YOU'RE OUT THERE?
- IT'S READY.
YOU CAN START ANYTIME.
- YOU MIGHT JUST THINK IT'S
ANOTHER EIGHT-SIX, TOHRU,
BUT I PROMISE YOU, THERE'S
NOTHING NORMAL ABOUT THIS CAR.
- OF COURSE, I KNOW THAT.
BUT I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO CONTROL
OVER WHAT HE'S DRIVING.
THE BEST I CAN DO IS TO JUST
GET OUT THERE AND RACE.
- HEY, TOHRU.
- SHINICHI, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
- HUH?
- CAN YOU FEEL THAT?
I'M SHAKING.
I'M SO SCARED.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
ALL I WANT TO DO RIGHT NOW
IS JUST RUN AWAY FROM HERE.
I KNOW THIS IS WEIRD, BUT AT
THE SAME TIME, I'M HAPPY.
I FEEL LIKE I CAN HARDLY
CONTROL MYSELF.
AND DO YOU KNOW WHY THAT IS?
IT'S BECAUSE OF PROJECT D.
I'VE BEEN DRIVING A LONG TIME,
AND IT'S A RARE THING TO HAVE
THE OPPORTUNITY TO RACE
UNDER PRESSURE LIKE THIS.
TONIGHT'S BATTLE,
IT'S GONNA BE THE MOST IMPORTANT
EVENT OF MY ENTIRE LIFE.
I'M THE REPRESENTATIVE OF THE
SEVEN STAR LEAF OUT THERE.
TONIGHT MY DRIVING WILL
MAKE YOU ALL PROUD.
NO REGRETS LEFT BEHIND.
- THAT'S HOW YOU'RE GONNA
WIN THIS. NOW, DO IT.
- ALRIGHT. THIS IS IT, GUYS.
LET'S MOVE OUT.
- ( engine revving )
- I'M TOHRU SUETSUGU.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- TAKUMI FUJIWARA.
- WHAT'S THIS FEELING?
I'VE NEVER FELT LIKE THIS
BEFORE. LIKE I'M NUMB.
PINS AND NEEDLES.
I'M SO NUMB I'M ALMOST
CRAWLING OUT OF MY SKIN!
NAO, YOU'RE GONNA TAKE CARE OF
ME ON THOSE ROADS, RIGHT?
- ( engines revving )
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU PROBABLY DON'T KNOW
THIS, TOHRU,
BUT YOU'RE THE REASON
I JOINED THIS TEAM.
YOU'RE THE BEST. THE DAREDEVIL
"KAMIKAZE DOWNHILLER".
THERE'S NOT A SINGLE
PERSON ALIVE
WHO COULD KEEP UP WITH YOU
ON THE DOWNHILL.
NOT NOW NOT EVER.
LOSING TO SOME
OUTSIDER EIGHT-SIX?
( scoffs ) AIN'T EVEN ON
THE BOOKS TONIGHT.
- I MADE THE RIGHT DECISION
IN CHOOSING TO LEAD.
YOU LOSE THAT RHYTHM ON THE
DOWNHILL, AND IT'LL KILL YA.
I WOULDN'T BE THE FIRST GUY
CARRIED OFF THIS MOUNTAIN.
- ( tires screeching )
- CALM DOWN. THIS ISN'T ABOUT
WINNING OR LOSING.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT MAXING
OUT MY FULL POTENTIAL.
- Ryosuke: WHEN YOU GET
RIGHT DOWN TO IT,
THE ROADSTER IS A MORE COMPACT
VEHICLE THAN THE EIGHT-SIX.
AND BECAUSE OF ITS
SMALLER SIZE...
YOU CAN BET THAT
THEIR MAIN WEAPON
WILL BE TECHNICAL FOOTWORK.
WHAT I'VE SEEN SO FAR TELLS ME
THIS GUY TOHRU'S
DRIVING IS ROUGH.
HE'S RELYING ON LEADING INTO
THE CORNERS AT HIGH SPEED.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S BAD FORM,
JUST KINDA ROOKIE IF YOU ASK ME.
THIS'LL PUSH HIS CAR
THROUGH EVERY CORNER,
BY USING AN INERTIAL DRIFT.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I UNDERSTAND THAT EVERY
DRIVING STYLE STARTS
WITH THE CONCEPT OF GOING INTO A
CORNER AS FAST AS POSSIBLE.
I JUST THINK THAT YOU COULD SAY
THAT HIS DRIVING TECHNIQUE WAS
ALMOST NURTURED BY HIS
UNDERPOWERED ROADSTER.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT
HE'S JUST LIKE FUJIWARA?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S VERY SIMILAR TO THE
RELATIONSHIP TAKUMI HAS
WITH HIS EIGHT-SIX.
WITH ONE EXCEPTION...
- YAHOO! ALRIGHT!
- THE BIG HIGHLIGHT OF THIS
COURSE IS THE STRETCH AT THE END
WHERE THERE ARE NO COVERS
OVER THE GUTTERS.
AND WHAT THE DRIVERS PULL OFF
AT THAT MOMENT
WILL MAKE THIS RACE.
YEAH BUT I WONDER,
IS THERE ANY WAY FOR A DRIVER
TO GET ACROSS THOSE PITS
WITHOUT JUST TRYING TO
AVOID THEM ALL TOGETHER?
THERE'S GOTTA BE
ANOTHER METHOD.
- YEAH. THERE IS.
I ALREADY TOLD TAKUMI ABOUT IT.
IT'S AN INCREDIBLY
DANGEROUS TECHNIQUE.
IT RELIES ON SHIFTING
THE CAR'S WEIGHT.
BUT IT'S NOTHING TAKUMI
AND KEISUKE CAN'T HANDLE.
I MEAN, HEY,
THEY ARE MY DOUBLE ACES.
- ( fast-paced song playing )
- WHOA, CHECK, THAT OUT! THAT
TURN HE JUST MADE IS INSANE.
TOHRU'S NOT GOING EASY TONIGHT!
BUT THEN AGAIN, LOOKS
LIKE THAT EIGHT-SIX
ISN'T FALLING TOO FAR BEHIND
EITHER, IS IT DUDE?
- HE WON'T LAST, THOUGH.
NOBODY CAN KEEP UP WITH TOHRU.
THAT GUY LEAVES
EVERYONE IN THE DUST.
- YEAH. THEN THERE'S ONLY
ONE QUESTION, RIGHT?
HOW LONG CAN THE
EIGHT-SIX KEEP UP?
- I BET HE'S OUT WAY BEFORE
THIS THING'S EVEN OVER.
- I GUESS I SHOULD START
BEING IMPRESSED.
NOBODY'S EVER BEEN ABLE TO STAY
SO CLOSE TO ME FOR THIS LONG.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE, THAT'S
NO NORMAL JUNKER EIGHT-SIX.
BUT EVEN MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THAT,
WHO THE HECK IS THE GUY
BEHIND THE WHEEL?
- YEAH, HE'S GOOD.
BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
I'M REALLY BEING PUSHED.
- I THINK THIS DUDE'S GOT
HIS HANDS FULL
JUST KEEPING UP WITH ME.
I CAN WIN THIS! I KNOW IT!
I'M NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN YOU PUSH TOO HARD
TRYING TO KEEP UP.
IF YOU VALUE YOUR LIFE, THEN YOU
SHOULD GIVE UP RIGHT NOW.
- HIS CORNERING IS INCREDIBLE,
BUT HE'S RECKLESS.
- RYOSUKE, THERE'S STILL
NO REAL DISTANCE BETWEEN THEM.
- SOUNDS RIGHT.
BECAUSE THIS IS WHERE IT BEGINS.
THE FASTEST DOWNHILL RACER
IN GUNMA
IS ABOUT TO SHOW HIS TEETH.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ WHO YOU WANNA BE,
WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA SEE,
WHAT YOU WANNA SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪