- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ( engine revving )
- Nobuhiko: STARTING IN
FIVE... FOUR...
THREE... TWO... ONE...
GO!
- ( tires screeching )
- SON OF A BITCH!
THIS GUY IS FAST!
- ARE THESE GUYS KIDDIN' AROUND
OR WHAT?
I'M MEAN A CAPPUCCINO'S
JUST A K, RIGHT?
A CAR LIKE THAT'S A JOKE.
WHO DO THESE GUYS
THINK THEY'RE RACIN'?
- YOU KIDDIN' ME? YOU REALLY
DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE UP TO?
A LOTTA FOLKS SAID
THE SAME THING
ABOUT TAKUMI'S
EIGHT-SIX LAST YEAR.
EVERYBODY IN GUNMA
THOUGHT HE WAS A JOKE.
HOW MANY OF THOSE
PEOPLE YOU THINK
ARE EATIN' THEIR WORDS NOW?
AN EIGHT-SIX DOESN'T HAVE CRAP
FOR TORQUE.
BUT BEFORE WE KNEW IT THAT THING
HANDED ALL OF US OUR ASSES.
THE NIGHT KIDS, THE RED SUNS,
PROJECT D.
I'LL TELL YOU WHO THESE GUYS
THINK THEY'RE RACIN'.
SOMEONE THEY CAN BEAT.
- ( tires screeching )
- SO THAT'S HOW YOU LEVEL THE
PLAYING FIELD, HUH?
BRING YOUR OWN
RAIN-MACHINE, TOO?
- OH, COME OFF IT, MAN.
THAT LITTLE BEAUTY'S GOT
THE EDGE IN THIS RACE
AND YOU KNOW IT.
- YEAH, WELL...
- YEAH, WELL, NOTHIN'.
THE BIG BAD D'S GONNA LOSE.
YOU WON'T SEE ME MARCHIN'
AROUND LIKE A CHAMPION
AFTER THIS, THOUGH.
I CAN PROMISE YOU THAT MUCH.
JUST BETWEEN THE TWO OF US,
SEEIN' YOUR BOY GETTING HIS
ASS HANDED TO HIM
BY A CAR LIKE THAT
MAKES ME FRIGGIN' SICK,
IT'S A DAMN TRAVESTY.
- YOU KNOW, YOU KEEP TALKIN'
LIKE IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE.
BUT YOU'VE RACED AGAINST HIM,
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S CAPABLE OF.
- I DO, YEAH. AND
I'M TELLIN' YOU
HE DOESN'T HAVE A
SNOWBALL'S CHANCE IN HELL.
- AND I'M TELLIN' YOU
YOU'RE FULL OF CRAP.
GRANTED, IF YOU LOOK AT
IT AS CAR VS. CAR,
THEN YEAH, THE
EIGHT-SIX IS TOAST.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT. BUT THERE'S
A FLESH-N'-BLOOD HUMAN BEING
BEHIND THE WHEEL OF
THAT EIGHT-SIX.
AND WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS RACE
AS DRIVER VS. DRIVER,
ALL BETS ARE OFF.
- SO WHAT?
YOU THINK WE CHERRY-PICKED
A DRIVER WHO'S GONNA SUCK?
SAKAMOTO'S A FREAK OF NATURE.
TAKE MY WORD FOR IT.
- YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT, DUDE.
I KNOW YOUR GUY'S GOTTA BE GOOD.
HE MIGHT EVEN BE A FREAK OF
NATURE LIKE YOU SAY, BUT...
WELL, LET ME PUT IT TO YOU
LIKE THIS,
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE
PROBABLY GONNA THINK
I'M JUST BLOWIN'
SMOKE UP YOUR ASS.
THEY HAVEN'T INVENTED
THE WORD YET
TO DESCRIBE WHATEVER
THE HELL TAKUMI IS.
NOTHING'S EVER WRITTEN IN STONE.
IF YOU'VE DRIVEN WITH HIM
YOU OUGHTA KNOW THAT.
THIS AIN'T OVER YET.
- Itsuki: AH, MAN,
THIS RAIN SUCKS!
I'M GETTIN' DRENCHED
TO THE BONE.
- Iketani: STOP BEING
A TITTY-BABY, WILL YA?
TAKUMI'S THE ONE HAVING TO RACE
IN THIS CRAP, NOT YOU.
I GOTTA ADMIT, THOUGH,
THE THOUGHT OF A DOWNHILL RACE
IN WEATHER LIKE THIS
MAKES ME CRINGE.
- JUST WHAT I THOUGHT!
HAVE YOU TWO NO FAITH AT ALL?
MAYBE YOUR KNEES LOCK
AT THE IDEA OF A LITTLE RAIN,
BUT DON'T FORGET WE'RE
TALKIN' ABOUT THE GUY
WHO KICKED BUTT ON MYOGI! HA-HA!
- WELL, YOU DO HAVE
A POINT THERE, I SUPPOSE.
- WELL, OF COURSE I DO! I'VE
EXPERIENCED HIS GODLIKE POWERS
FIRSTHAND, HAVEN'T I? ( laughs )
WHEN YOU GET DOWN TO IT, I'M
SURPRISED THE RAIN EVEN BOTHERS
TO FALL IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- ( engine revving )
- ( tires screeching )
- Nobuhiko: WHICH DO YOU PREFER?
LEADING OR CHASING?
- Sakamoto: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
LEAD CAR'S UNDER MORE PRESSURE
TO SET THE PACE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT'S RAINING
LIKE THIS.
I MEAN, THERE'S NO
POINT IN DOING THIS
IF IT'S GONNA BE EASY, RIGHT?
CHASING ISN'T EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'D CALL OUR STYLE.
BESIDES, I DON'T WANNA TAKE
ALL NIGHT.
I'M GONNA END IT
BY THE FIRST RUN.
- THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR.
OKAY THEN. YOU LEAD.
BUT END IT QUICKLY.
- YOU'LL SEE FOR YOURSELF
ONCE THE RACE STARTS,
THAT PINK MONSTROSITY
IN FRONT OF YOU
IS IN FACT LUDICROUSLY FAST.
IT'LL DUST YOU ON THE CORNERS,
SO TRY TO COMPENSATE ON
THE STRAIGHTAWAYS.
DON'T MAKE THE MISTAKE
OF THINKING THIS RACE'LL
BE LIKE ANY OF THE
OTHERS YOU'VE RUN.
- ( engines revving )
- HERE'S SOME ADVICE FOR YOU.
IMAGINE THE MOST DIFFICULT
SITUATION YOU'VE BEEN IN
BEHIND THE WHEEL OF THAT CAR
AND INVERT IT. TO WIN
THIS THING YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
TURN THE GOLDEN
RULE ON ITS HEAD
AND DO UNTO OTHERS
WHAT'S BEEN DONE TO YOU.
THINK ABOUT KYOICHI SUDOU.
HE AND THE EMPERORS.
HOW DO YOU THINK THEY COPE WITH
MESSY CONDITIONS LIKE THESE?
THAT'LL BE THE KEY
TO YOUR STRATEGY.
AND BEAR IN MIND THE POINT HERE
IS TO DO THE OPPOSITE OF WHAT
YOU'D NORMALLY DO.
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW HAS TO
BE LOOKED AT IN REVERSE.
- Matsumoto: IS IT JUST ME,
OR ARE YOU CHANGING THE WAY
YOU GIVE TAKUMI ADVICE?
SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE GETTIN' A
LITTLE ABSTRACT WITH HIM LATELY.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- YEAH, I DO. I MEAN,
UP TILL RECENTLY WHENEVER
YOU GAVE HIM POINTERS
YOU'D LAY IT OUT LIKE
AN INSTRUCTION MANUAL.
"DO THIS, DO THAT."
YOU KNOW, REAL SPECIFIC STUFF,
BUT TONIGHT, I GUESS... I DUNNO.
YOU KINDA POSED IT
LIKE A RIDDLE.
DON'T GET ME WRONG,
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
INSTEAD OF JUST HAVING
IT SPELLED OUT,
HE'S GOTTA USE THE OLD
NOGGIN FOR HIMSELF.
- I GUESS THAT JUST GOES TO SHOW
HOW MUCH TAKUMI'S GROWN LATELY.
SEE, IT'S BEEN MY AIM TO TRY
AND SET UP THESE RACES
SO THAT HE AND KEISUKE FACE
SOMETHING A LITTLE DIFFERENT,
A LITTLE MORE CHALLENGING,
EACH TIME OUT.
- I SUSPECTED
THAT MIGHT BE THE IDEA.
YOU'RE FORCING THEM TO MATURE.
AND MAYBE IT'S PATTING MY OWN
BACK AS MUCH AS YOURS TO SAY IT,
BUT PROJECT D'S
DONE 'EM SOME GOOD.
- I HOPE SO.
I MIGHT'VE GONE A LITTLE
OVERBOARD TONIGHT, THOUGH.
WHEN YOU'RE COMPETING,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE A HELLUVA
LOT OF CHANCES.
YOU SAY I WAS
A LITTLE BIT ABSTRACT.
I SAY I MIGHT'VE SENT TAKUMI
OUT THERE HALF-COCKED.
- ( engine revving )
- ♪ DRIVIN' CRAZY ♪
- I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THE WAY THIS GUY
HANDLES THAT PIECE OF CRAP.
HOW IN THE HELL
AM I SUPPOSED TO KEEP UP?
- ♪ DRIVIN' CRAZY ♪
- DAMMIT! I CAN'T CATCH UP
TO HIM ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS
WHEN I CAN'T EVEN CORNER
AT THE PACE THIS GUY'S SETTIN'.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THIS IS JUST PATHETIC.
- Kenta: SORRY. I'M STILL
NOT REALLY FOLLOWIN' YA HERE.
- USE YOUR HEAD. HOW MUCH
DOES THE EIGHT-SIX WEIGH?
- I GUESS 950 KILOGRAMS OR SO?
- EXACTLY. THE WHOLE THING
WEIGHS JUST UNDER A TON.
BUT THE CAPPUCCINO
IS EVEN LIGHTER.
AT MOST
WE'RE TALKING AROUND 700.
- YEAH. SO?
- THAT'S A 250-KILOGRAM
DIFFERENCE.
THE LESS A CAR WEIGHS,
THE EASIER IT IS TO CONTROL.
THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T SEE
ANY BIG CLUNKERS RACING.
THEIR INERTIA HOLDS 'EM BACK.
IT'S BASIC PHYSICS.
- BUT YOU CAN'T FINE-TUNE
A CAPPUCCINO
LIKE YOU CAN AN
EIGHT-SIX, CAN YOU?
I MEAN,
LIGHTWEIGHT'S ALL IT'S GOT.
- DOESN'T MATTER HOW MUCH
YOU TRY TO FINE-TUNE IT.
LIGHTER'S ALWAYS BETTER.
- COME ON, MAN. YOU DON'T THINK
TAKUMI'S GONNA LOSE.
- KENTA, WHAT DO I
KEEP TELLING YOU
ABOUT JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS?
I'VE SAID IT BEFORE.
WHENEVER TAKUMI'S RACING,
ALL BETS ARE OFF.
- JUST FOCUS ON THAT
SWEET FRICTION
BETWEEN THE TREADS
AND THE ROAD, DUDE.
THOSE CORNERS LOVE
THIS FRIGGIN' LITTLE CAR,
BUT DON'T GET RECKLESS.
THIS THING'LL HYDROPLANE
LIKE A LEAF.
UNTIL THE DAY SOME
GENIUS INVENTS A CAR
THAT CAN HANDLE SPEED
IN WHATEVER CONDITIONS
YOU THROW AT IT,
JUST KEEP DOIN' WHAT YOU DO.
COMPENSATE FOR LACK
OF UNDERSTEER
BY DIGGIN' INTO THE OVERSTEER
AT THE START OF EACH CORNER
LIKE THE BADASS YOU ARE.
THAT'S HOW IT'S DONE!
FOUR-WHEEL DRIFT, BABY.
RALLY STYLE!
DAMN IT. HOW'S HE STAYING
ON ME LIKE THIS?
BASTARD'S RIGHT UP MY ASS.
THIS RAIN'S A BITCH, THAT'S WHY.
EVEN I'M HOLDIN' BACK A LITTLE
'CAUSE OF IT.
IT'S JUST TOO BIG A GAMBLE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW MUCH LEEWAY YOU'VE GOT
WHEN YOU'RE BRAKING.
CAN'T WIN IF YOU CRASH.
I SURE AS HELL HOPE THIS CRAZY
SON OF A BITCH GETS THAT.
THIS TAG-ALONG CRAP
IS GONNA GET BOTH OF US KILLED.
- ♪ I FEEL LIKE DRIVIN' CRAZY ♪
♪ RUNNIN' THROUGH YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ THE SPEED OF THE FIRE ♪
♪ DRIVIN' CRAZY ♪
♪ RAGE IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE NIGHT ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- I WISH I HAD KNOWN.
ABOUT WHAT THESE GUYS
HAD UP THEIR SLEEVES, I MEAN.
I ONLY FOUND OUT
THE DAY BEFORE YESTERDAY.
AND TO BE HONEST, I FEEL
PAINTED INTO A CORNER.
LIKE I MIGHT'VE
MADE A MISTAKE. SO...
- YOU MAKE A MISTAKE?
AH, COME ON. WHEN'S
THE LAST TIME THAT HAPPENED?
- TONIGHT FOR ONE.
HELL, I SCREW UP CONSTANTLY.
I'M JUST REALLY GOOD
AT BLUFFING MY WAY OUT OF IT.
I HAVE BEEN LATELY.
WHEN I GET THINGS RIGHT IT'S
MORE LUCK THAN ANYTHING ELSE,
SOME UNPREDICTABLE FACTOR
USUALLY MAKES AN APPEARANCE,
WASHES AWAY ANY SIGNS OF MY
POOR JUDGMENT, SO TO SPEAK.
- WASHES THEM ALL AWAY, HUH?
- I'M DRAWIN' A COMPLETE BLANK.
WHAT WAS RYOSUKE TRYING
TO TELL ME BACK THERE?
HOW WOULD KYOICHI AND HIS CREW
HANDLE CONDITIONS LIKE THESE?
HE SAID TRY AND MAKE UP FOR THE
CORNERS ON THE STRAIGHTAWAYS,
BUT HOW?
THAT CAR WEIGHS
NEXT TO NOTHING.
HOW CAN I OVERTAKE SOMEONE WHEN
I CAN'T EVEN MATCH THEIR SPEED?
- IF ANYTHING MAKES UP
FOR MY MISTAKE TONIGHT,
IT'LL BE THIS DOWNPOUR.
- BUT I'M NOT SURE
THAT MAKES ANY SENSE, RYOSUKE.
THE RAIN'S JUST GONNA
MAKE THINGS HARDER FOR HIM.
AT LEAST THAT'S
THE THEORY ANYWAY.
SORRY, I DON'T MEAN
TO SECOND-GUESS YOU.
BUT THE WETTER THE PAVEMENT,
THE HARDER IT IS FOR THE TIRES
TO KEEP A GOOD GRIP
ON THE CORNERS.
SEEMS TO ME LIKE THAT'D MAKE
THE DIFFERENCE IN WEIGHT
BETWEEN THE TWO CARS
EVEN MORE OF AN ADVANTAGE
FOR OUR OPPONENTS.
- AH, BUT THERE'S A BLIND SPOT
IN THE THEORY.
IF WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT A CIRCUIT RACE
IN BROAD DAYLIGHT, THEN YEAH,
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY DEAD-ON.
BUT RAIN ON MOUNTAIN PASS AT
NIGHT IS A DIFFERENT ANIMAL,
ONE THAT TESTS A
DRIVER'S INNATE SKILL,
NOT JUST HOW HE HANDLES
A PARTICULAR CAR.
ANY SIMULATION OF A RACE
UNDER CONDITIONS LIKE THESE
WOULD HAVE TO
TAKE INTO ACCOUNT MATTERS
BEYOND PURE TECHNIQUE.
- LIKE WHAT?
- LIKE HOW A DRIVER EVOLVES.
TAKUMI'S STRENGTH
IS HIS ABILITY TO ADAPT.
IF HE CAN FIND A WAY TO USE
THIS RAIN TO HIS ADVANTAGE,
THEN THE EIGHT-SIX'S RELATIVE
WEIGHT CAN GIVE HIM THE EDGE.
BUT LIKE I SAID, WHEN
I GET THINGS RIGHT
IT'S USUALLY BECAUSE OF LUCK,
HIS LUCK.
- I THINK I CAN
CATCH UP WITH HIM
AT THE END OF THIS STRAIGHTAWAY.
SO I CAN MATCH HIS PACE.
I'LL BE DAMNED.
STILL NEW TERRITORY
FOR ME, THOUGH.
WINNING ON POWER ONLY TO GET
MY ASS BEAT ON THE CORNERS.
THIS IS FRIGGIN' PATHETIC.
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO STRESSED.
TO THINK I'VE GOTTA RELY ON
STRAIGHTAWAYS IN A DOWNHILL RUN.
- ( boosting )
MEANWHILE THE
SMUG LITTLE BASTARD
IS DRIFTING LIKE A
FEATHER IN THE WIND.
GOD, I WANNA PUT THE PRESSURE
ON HIM SO BAD I CAN TASTE IT!
WHAT A MINUTE!
THAT'S WHAT KYOICHI DOES.
YEAH, IT'S GOTTA BE!
- DUDE, ARE YOU SEEING THIS?
THAT CAPPUCCINO IS FLYIN'!
- THAT EIGHT-SIX IS
HAVING A HARD TIME
JUST KEEPING UP WITH IT.
- I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SAY THIS,
BUT PROJECT D JUST
MIGHT BE SCREWED.
- OKAY, HERE COMES
MY LITTLE TRIBUTE
TO KYOICHI'S IDEA OF FAIR PLAY.
I'VE GOTTA CLOSE THE GAP BETWEEN
US FOR THIS TO WORK,
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
GET READY, ASSHOLE.
WE'RE ABOUT TO GET REAL COZY.
- HE'S STILL ON HIM? HOW
THE HELL IS HE MANAGING THAT?
- ( van engine starts )
- ALL RIGHT. WHATEVER, DUDE,
JUST KEEP ME POSTED. COOL.
( hangs up phone )
HEY, THEY JUST PASSED THROUGH
THE HAIRPIN CANYON.
HE SAYS THE GAP BETWEEN 'EM
IS ONLY ABOUT 10 OR 15 METERS.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE EIGHT-SIX SHOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO KEEP UP WITH THE CAPPUCCINO
FOR AS LONG AS IT HAS.
- ( wind howling )
- THE RACE CAN'T
BE GOING LIKE THIS,
NOT ACCORDING TO MY SIMULATION.
THE RAIN WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
OUR ACE IN THE HOLE!
IF SAKAMOTO CAN'T SHAKE HIM
ON THE INCLINES,
HE'LL MISS HIS WINDOW.
ONCE THE ROAD LEVELS OFF,
IT'S ANYBODY'S GUESS WHO'LL
TAKE THE LEAD.
I'VE MADE A MISTAKE.
- HUH?
- I'M AFRAID THE EIGHT-SIX'S
DRIVER IS THROWING
THE PROVERBIAL
MONKEY-WRENCH
INTO WHAT, BY MY
CALCULATIONS AT LEAST,
SHOULD HAVE BEEN A
SUREFIRE VICTORY.
- I'VE GOT HIM! I CAN FEEL IT
BY THE WAY THE EIGHT-SIX
IS RESPONDING TO ME.
THE TREADS MIGHT AS WELL BE
FUSED TO MY NERVOUS SYSTEM.
IT'S LIKE I'M GRIPPING THE WET
PAVEMENT WITH MY OWN BARE HANDS.
- ( water splashing )
- HELL, IN THIS BABY I CAN
PRACTICALLY TELL YOU
HOW MUCH WATER THE TIRES
ARE SPRAYING,
DOWN TO THE DROP.
ALL RIGHT,
TIME TO STOP SCREWIN' AROUND.
STAY IN THE ZONE, DUDE. THERE
ARE ONLY ONE OR TWO PLACES LEFT
WHERE YOU CAN INITIATE
A COUNTER-ATTACK.
- THERE IS ONE THING
THAT WORRIES ME.
- HMM?
- SURELY THE FIRST THING THAT
COMES TO MIND
WHEN YOU THINK
OF KYOICHI'S STYLE
IS HIS COUNTER ATTACKS, RIGHT?
- PROBABLY.
- THAT'S JUST IT.
I MEAN, TAKUMI'S BOUND TO BE
CONFUSED OUT THERE
HE'S GONNA MAKE
THE SAME ASSUMPTION,
TRYING TO PULL OFF
A COUNTERATTACK IN THIS WEATHER
WOULD BE BAD NEWS.
- IT CERTAINLY WOULD BE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION
PRETTY WELL.
IF THAT'S HOW HE CHOOSES
TO INTERPRET WHAT I SAID,
THERE'LL BE NEXT TO NO CHANCE
OF HIS WINNING.
- YOU GOTTA BE SHITTIN' ME!
WATARU'S EIGHT-SIX COULDN'T HOLD
A CANDLE TO THIS BABY.
WHAT THE HELL?
AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
HOW IS THIS GUY SO DAMN FAST?
JACKASS IS GOIN' AT IT
LIKE THE ROAD'S DRY AS A BONE,
WHILE IT'S ALL I CAN DO
NOT TO HYDROPLANE.
I CAN'T PUSH IT ANYMORE.
ROAD'S JUST TOO DAMN DANGEROUS.
YOU'RE NOT WUSSIN' OUT.
YOU'RE STAYIN' ALIVE.
- I HATE WEATHER LIKE THIS.
ONE LITTLE MISTAKE AND BOOM,
EVEN THE BEST DRIVERS'LL
CRASH AND BURN.
RAIN REDUCES THE WHOLE THING
TO A CRAP SHOOT.
REALLY DOESN'T MATTER
HOW GOOD YOU ARE.
SAKAMOTO'S CRAZY,
BUT THE MAN'S NOBODY'S FOOL.
EVEN HE'S GONNA
SECOND-GUESS HIMSELF
IN A FRIGGIN' DOWNPOUR
LIKE THIS ONE.
AT LEAST I SURE HOPE SO.
I HOPE BOTH OF 'EM DO,
FOR THAT MATTER.
I MEAN, HELL.
NOBODY WANTS TO SEE
TWO GOOD DRIVERS WASTED
OVER A STUPID RACE LIKE THIS.
JUST TRY TO IMAGINE
WHAT IT MUST BE LIKE
FOR THE TWO OF 'EM OUT THERE.
LIKE A WHITE-KNUCKLED
RIDE THROUGH HELL.
GOD KNOWS IT WOULD BE FOR ME.
- DAMN IT! WHAT THE HELL'S
WITH THIS GUY?
GET OFF MY ASS ALREADY, DUDE.
IT'S STARTIN' TO FREAK ME OUT.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE
ANY FREAKIN' SENSE!
- ♪ RAISING HELL ♪
- DEJA VU. THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT
IT WAS LIKE WHEN I RACED KYOICHI
ON THE IROHA SLOPES.
WHEN THE GUY YOU'RE UP
AGAINST CAN DRIFT FASTER,
IT'S BEST TO JUST LET HIM
HAVE THE CORNERS.
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO IS BRAKE,
GET YOUR BEARINGS,
AND BE READY TO HIT
THE ACCELERATOR
RIGHT OUT OF THE TURN.
THE ONLY WAY TO OVERTAKE
HIM IS TO FLOOR IT
EVEN LONGER THAN HE DOES.
- ♪ AND THE WILD HEART BEATING ♪
♪ DANCING THROUGH
THE HEAT AND DARK ♪
♪ THE DEVIL WILL GETCHA ♪
♪ COMING TO YOU ♪
♪ FASTER, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ HARDER, GO RAISING HELL ♪
- I CAN'T HELP IT, ALl RIGHT?
THE WHOLE SITUATION
BUGS THE SHIT OUT OF ME.
NO POINT IN DENYING IT.
THESE DOUCHE BAGS
ARE JUST A BUNCH OF CHEATERS
WITH AN AXE TO GRIND.
- THERE'S NOTHING IN THE
RULEBOOK SAYS
THEY CAN'T USE A
LIGHTWEIGHT VEHICLE.
- DON'T STAND THERE AND ACT LIKE
LOSING TO THESE JERKS
WOULDN'T MAKE YOUR SKIN CRAWL.
IF TAKUMI LETS HIMSELF
GET BEAT,
I'M GONNA KNOCK HIS ASS
INTO NEXT TUESDAY.
- WELL, IT'S GOOD TO SEE
YOU'RE KEEPING A COOL HEAD.
LOOK, ALL I'M TRYING
TO SAY IS THAT
HE'S GOT HIS WORK CUT
OUT FOR HIM, OKAY?
I JUST HOPE THE RAIN GIVES HIM
THAT LITTLE EXTRA PUSH
RYOSUKE SEEMS TO THINK IT WILL.
THE SECOND HALF OF THE
COURSE IS COMING UP,
SO HE'LL HAVE A GOOD CHANCE OF
OVERTAKING HIM SOON.
THERE'S NEXT TO NO INCLINE
ON THAT SECTION
AND THE STRAIGHTAWAYS
ARE EVEN LONGER.
HE SHOULD KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- YOU DO FIND THIS IRONIC,
DON'T YOU?
- HOW COULD I NOT?
TAKUMI HAS TO LOOK AT EVERYTHING
HE KNOWS ABOUT RACING BACKWARDS.
EVERY OPPONENT'S STYLE,
EVERY TACTIC.
IT'S ALL SWITCHED AROUND.
UP TO THIS POINT,
THE DOWNHILL HAS ALWAYS
BEEN TAKUMI'S ALLY,
BUT NOW IT'S THE ONE
PLACE HE CAN'T GET
THE LEAST BIT OF LEVERAGE.
- ♪ FASTER, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ HARDER, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ ROCKING, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ ROLLING, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ FASTER, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ HARDER, GO RAISING HELL ♪
♪ WE'RE GONNA YELL ♪
♪ AND STORM SPREAD THIS FIRE ♪
- HE'S NOT AFRAID OF ANYTHING,
IS HE?
DUDE'S RIDIN' ME CLOSE ENOUGH
THE SPRAY MUST BE TOTALLY
BLOCKING HIS HEADLIGHTS.
THAT'S WHY I CHOSE TO LEAD.
LOW VISIBILITY'S NOT MY BAG.
BETWEEN THE RAIN AND THE DARK,
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
YOU CAN SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOIN'.
AND THE CLOSER YOU GET,
THE WORSE IT'S GONNA BE.
- ( revving )
- ♪ RAISING HELL ♪
- HE'S GAINING ON ME? BUT HOW?
HOW COULD ANYONE FOLLOW
MY LINE IN THESE CONDITIONS?
THIS GUY CAN'T BE FOR REAL!
WHAT KIND OF DEMON
AM I UP AGAINST?
- ( Nobody Reason playing )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON ♪
♪ THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
( rapping in Japanese )
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON ♪
♪ THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
- ( continues singing
in Japanese )
- ♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE ♪
♪ WHERE IS THE END ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE ♪
♪ WHERE IS THE END ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS ♪
♪ THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪
( singing in Japanese )