- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ALL RIGHT.
- Man: SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
I HEAR JOUSHIMA AND HOSHINO ARE
COMIN' OUT TONIGHT.
IT'S WEIRD, MAN.
FOR THE TWO PILLARS OF PURPLE
SHADOW TO GET TOGETHER,
IT'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING BIG.
- YOU MEAN YOU REALLY
HADN'T HEARD?
PROJECT D'S HEADIN' UP
TO CHALLENGE US.
- YOU GOTTA BE YANKIN' MY CHAIN.
YOU MEAN JOUSHIMA AND HOSHINO
ARE RACING PROJECT D THEMSELVES?
- I KINDA DOUBT THEY WILL.
I'M GUESSING THEY'LL PUT UP THE
YOUNGER DUDES IN PURPLE SHADOW
BEFORE THEY DO THAT.
THOSE GUYS HAVE BETTER THINGS TO
DO THAN RACE A COUPLE OF KIDS.
I MEAN THEY'RE LIKE
GODS ON THE ROAD.
THEY WON'T GET THEIR HANDS
DIRTY WITH THIS ONE.
- HERE THEY ARE.
JOUSHIMA "GOD ARM" TOSHIYA AND
KOUZOU "GOD FOOT" HOSHINO.
- ( sighs )
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
PUTTING ON A FEW POUNDS, BUDDY.
YOU DON'T LOWER THAT
CHOLESTEROL SOON,
IT'LL KILL YOU FASTER THAN
A FIRE IN YOUR GAS TANK.
- AH, GET OFF MY CASE.
I LIVE MY LIFE THICK AND QUICK,
YOU KNOW THAT.
ANYWAY, WHEN HAVE YOU
KNOWN ME TO LISTEN
TO WHAT SOME DUMBASS
DOCTOR HAS TO SAY?
- ( laughs ) YEAH.
YOU AND ME BOTH, BIG GUY.
- SO PROJECT D, HUH?
I HAVEN'T BEEN THIS JAZZED ABOUT
A RACE IN A REAL LONG TIME.
MAYBE GUYS LIKE US JUST GET
EASIER TO EXCITE
THE OLDER WE GET.
BUT WHO CARES,
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- I DON'T WANNA SOUND
LIKE A JERK OR ANYTHING, BUT
I DIDN'T THINK YOU GUYS
WERE GOING TO SHOW UP.
ARE YOU TWO GONNA RACE?
- THAT'S RIGHT. I HOPE IT'S
NOT A PROBLEM FOR YOU.
- OF COURSE NOT.
NOT A PROBLEM AT ALL.
YOU TWO CAN DO
WHAT YOU WANT.
IT'S JUST THAT THE MOST SENIOR
MEMBERS DON'T NEED TO WASTE
THEIR TIME RACING A BUNCH OF
KIDS IF THEY DON'T WANT TO.
- US RACING THIS HAS GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH AGE.
THESE FELLAS ARE DRIVING ALL THE
WAY UP HERE FROM GUNMA RIGHT?
IT'S A LONG WAY. LETS GIVE THEM
A WARM IBARAKI WELCOME.
SOUND GOOD TO YOU?
- WELL, SURE. BUT WE'RE
BETTER THAN THESE GUYS,
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF
THEM FOR YOU.
- EASE OFF OF THE ATTITUDE.
JUST LET US DRIVE THIS ONE,
AND I'LL GUARANTEE YOU'LL
LIKE WHAT YOU SEE.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE A
COUPLE OF ARROGANT JERKS
WHO JUST SHOWED UP
ON YOUR SCENE
TO TELL YOU THE WAY OF THE WORLD
AND HOW TO DRIVE ITS ROADS.
WE FORMED PURPLE SHADOW
A LONG TIME AGO
AND TAUGHT YOU A HELL OF A LOT
WHEN WE BROUGHT YOU KIDS ON.
BUT THE FACT IS WE'RE
GETTIN' UP THERE.
WE CAN'T KEEP UP WITH YOU
YOUNG KIDS ANYMORE.
- HOSHINO, THAT JUST ISN'T TRUE.
YOU KNOW NOT ONE OF US HAS COME
NEAR YOUR LEVEL OF EXPERTISE.
- STOP BEING SO MODEST.
YOU LOOK LIKE A DOUCHE.
YOU'RE A REGULAR ON
THE TSUKUBA CIRCUIT,
AND YOU MAKE ALL OF THOSE CATS
LOOK LIKE FAT-CHEWING CHUMPS.
- THE TWO OF US JUST DIG
DOING CRAP LIKE THIS
AND WE DON'T GET TO THAT MUCH.
NO MATTER HOW OLD WE GET, WE'RE
STILL JUST TWO KIDS WITH CARS.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE TAKE
'EM FOR A FEW MORE RUNS?
- SURE. GOT CHIP THIS RUST
OFF OF OURSELVES
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER RIGHT.
- RUST? IF THOSE GUYS
THINK THEY'RE RUSTY,
I'D HATE TO KNOW
WHAT THEY THINK ABOUT US.
THEY BOTH HAVE THEIR SKILLS
HONED EVEN SHARPER
THAN A SAMURAI SWORD.
GOD ARM. EARNED HIS NAME BY
MASTERING THE METHOD
OF ONE HANDED STEERING.
DR. TOSHIYA JOUSHIMA.
AND THEN THERE'S
KOUZOU "GOD FOOT" HOSHINO.
HE GOT HIS NAME BECAUSE OF
HIS ACCELERATOR TECHNIQUES.
ONLY SOMEONE OF A
FOOT OF A GOD
COULD DO WHAT HE DOES
WITH THOSE PEDALS.
AFTER COUNTLESS BATTLES,
THESE TWO MEN ARE THE GODS
OF THE MOUNTAIN PASS.
THEY HAVE NO EQUAL.
- ( phone ringing )
- Takumi: DAD, YOU GONNA
GET THAT?
- ( ringing continues )
- GUESS HE'S NOT HERE.
FUJIWARA TOFU SHOP,
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- HEY, IT'S WATARU.
I'M IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT WANNA GRAB
A BITE TO EAT SOMEWHERE.
SO, WHAT'S YOUR
NEXT BIG DESTINATION?
- IBARAKI.
- RIGHT ON.
- SO, WATARU,
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
YOU HELPED ME OUT WITH.
I THOUGHT A LOT ABOUT WHAT YOU
SAID AND I THINK I'M GETTING IT.
- GLAD TO HEAR IT HELPED OUT.
THAT DOESN'T ALWAYS HAPPEN
WHEN I GIVE ADVICE.
- IT'S LIKE I FINALLY
FEEL LIKE I'M STARTING
TO WRAP MY HEAD AROUND THE
EIGHT-SIX FOR THE FIRST TIME.
- HERE IT COMES. I WONDER
WHAT HE'S GONNA
START BABBLING ABOUT THIS TIME.
SERIOUSLY, DUDE, SOME OF THE
CRAP THAT COMES OUT OF
YOUR MOUTH SOMETIMES
MAKES NO FREAKIN' SENSE.
- HEY I'M ONLY BEING HONEST.
I FEEL LIKE I FINALLY GOT
A HANDLE ON HER.
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS
I KNOW WHAT I GOT TO DO
IF I WANT HER TO PERFORM
AT HER FULL POTENTIAL.
IT'S LIKE HOW, I AUTOMATICALLY
KNOW WHAT TO DO
TO CONQUER A COURSE THE
FIRST TIME OUT...
OR HOW TO BALANCE THE
SUPPORT ON MY SUSPENSION.
I'M JUST NOW STARTING TO FEEL MY
GRIP ON THOSE KINDS OF THINGS.
THAT'S ALL I'M TRYING SAY.
- WHATEVER FLOATS YOUR BOAT.
AT LEAST YOUR MAKING
PROGRESS, RIGHT?
STILL, IT BLOWS MY MIND.
HOW ANYONE COULD DO
WHAT YOU'VE DONE
WITH AS LITTLE INFORMATION
AS YOU'VE HAD UP TO NOW
IS A MYSTERY.
- YEAH I GUESS BUT THAT
DOESN'T MEAN I'M STUPID.
I'M JUST WAITING ON THE DAY
I LOSE A RACE
SO I CAN UNDERSTAND
HER EVEN BETTER.
THAT EIGHT-SIX...
- Matsumoto: WHAT'S WITH
THE ADDED MANPOWER?
WHY WE BRINGING THE EXTRA
SUPPORT CAR WITH US THIS TIME?
- BEFORE WE CAME OUT, RYOSUKE
AND I MADE A LIST OF EVERYTHING
WE KNEW WE'D NEED.
WHEN WE LOOKED AT IT ALL
SIDE-BY-SIDE,
TURNED OUT THREE CARS
WASN'T GONNA BE ENOUGH.
I JUST WANTED EVERYBODY HERE TO
KNOW WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
UP THE ANTE
AGAINST THESE GUYS.
NOW LET THAT SINK IN REAL GOOD.
WE'VE GOT A LONG
HAUL AHEAD OF US,
SO BE CAREFUL OUT THERE. GOT IT?
- GOT IT.
- ( engine starting )
- LET'S ROLL.
- Sakai: HEY, CHIEF,
DID YOU HEAR?
PROJECT D'S NEXT OPPONENT
IS THE PURPLE SHADOW.
THEY'RE GONNA BE
RACING IN IBARAKI.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS NUTS
BUT I ALSO HEARD
IT WAS GONNA BE HOSHINO
AND JOUSHIMA IN THE BATTLE.
- NO SHIT.
IF YOU CAN FIND THE TIME
IN YOUR BUSY SCHEDULES,
BOTH OF YOU NEED TO GO WATCH
THESE GUYS BATTLE THE D.
- BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT PURPLE SHADOW
WAS ANYTHING TO RIDE HOME ABOUT.
- DAIKI, WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW
COULD FILL A LIBRARY.
BOTH OF THOSE GUYS ARE
DRIVERS CHIEF HERE
WOULD TAKE HIS HAT
OFF TO ANY DAY.
- NO KIDDIN'.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DOES PROJECT D EVEN STAND A
CHANCE ON THIS ONE?
- THE PENDULUM IS ALWAYS
SWINGING, BOYS.
WHO KNOWS WHERE IT'S
GONNA COME BACK TO?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT WHAT
YOU CAN'T CONTROL.
JUST WATCH THE MATCH.
TAKE AWAY WHAT YOU CAN.
SEE HOW THESE GUYS TACKLE
SUCH AN ENORMOUS OBSTACLE
AND THINK ABOUT HOW
YOU WOULD DO IT.
THAT'S THE THING I WANT
YOU CAN TAKE AWAY.
- ( cars approaching )
- HERE WE GO.
- Hoshino: ALL THAT
SOUNDS FINE.
AND WE'LL DO EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO MAKE SURE THE NIGHT
RUNS SMOOTHLY FOR YOUR CREW.
- WE APPRECIATE THAT.
- SURE.
- IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU.
- THESE KIDS ARE A
HECK OF A LOT NICER
THAN I'D THOUGHT THEY BE.
- THAT'S WHAT I WAS THINKING.
AFTER WHAT I SAW
ON THEIR HOMEPAGE,
I EXPECTED A BUNCH OF BAGGY PANT
WEARING, ARROGANT LITTLE PRICKS.
- I'M GETTING A GOOD VIBE.
NOW THAT WE KNOW THEY'RE
COOL, WE CAN SKIP THE MIND GAMES
AND ATTITUDE AND JUST GO
STRAIGHT TO THE RACING.
- THIS'LL BE A FUN NIGHT.
COULD BE THE BEST WE'VE
HAD IN A LONG TIME.
- YOU KNOW THE ROUTINE. FIRST
COUPLE OF RUNS AT 80%.
STAY FOCUSED, ALL RIGHT?
- ( engines revving )
- ( upbeat song playing )
- ♪ THIS TIME YOU'LL LIKE ♪
- Kenta: WHOA!
HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH
THE FOURTH VAN HERE?
YOU GOT IT FILLED UP WITH ALMOST
NOTHING ELSE BUT SPARE TIRES.
WELL, EXPECT FOR
THIS MOTOR SCOOTER.
WHAT'S THAT DOING IN HERE?
- OH THAT, I BROUGHT THAT ALONG
FOR OUR DRIVERS TO USE.
- WHY FOR THEM?
- SO THEY CAN CHECK OUT
THE COURSE.
IT'LL BE AVAILABLE TO 'EM
ANYTIME THEY WANNA USE IT
BEFORE DARK TOMORROW.
ON THAT SCOOTER, THEY'LL BE
ABLE TO SEE ANY DAMAGE
OR PROBLEM SPOTS
THE ROAD A LOT EASIER.
- THEN HOPEFULLY THEY'LL BE
ABLE TO DRAW OUT A MORE
DETAILED PLAN OF THE COURSE
BEFORE THEY'RE LOADED FOR BEAR.
I MEAN IT'D BE BEST IF THEY
COULD WALK THE ROAD,
BUT WE DON'T HAVE
THAT KINDA TIME.
THIS IS JUST ONE OF THE
NEW IDEAS RYOSUKE CAME UP WITH.
- IT'S SMART.
HE'S BEEN KICKIN' OUT A LOT OF
KILLER IDEAS LATELY, HASN'T HE?
- JUST WHEN THE OLD TRICKS
WON'T WORK.
SO THIS NEW CREW'S GOTTA
BE PRETTY GOOD.
- ( machine whirring )
- ALL DONE.
OK, YOU'RE LOCKED IN.
BALANCE SEEMS FINE AND THE
SUSPENSION'S SOLID.
JUST DO ME A FAVOR AND KEEP AN
EYE ON HOW YOUR TRACTION
HOLDS UP OUT THERE.
- COOL. WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- HOW'S THE CAR
LOOKIN' TONIGHT?
- LIKE A GREASED PISTON.
AND TAKUMI SEEMS TO HAVE
HIS HEAD SCREWED ON TIGHT.
THINK HE'S FINALLY CATCHIN' ON
TO A FEW OF THE THINGS IT TAKES
TO SET UP HIS CAR
BEFORE A RACE.
HE ISN'T THE SAME DUMB KID
HE USED TO BE.
- I'VE BEEN NOTICING THE
DIFFERENCE TOO.
I WAS JUST THINKIN'
HOW FAR HE'S COME
SINCE HIS FIRST RACE
WITH PROJECT D.
HE'S PRACTICING A LOT OUTSIDE
OF HIS TIMES WITH US,
TIMES WHEN WE CAN'T
KEEP OUR EYES ON HIM.
WHATEVER HE'S DOING,
HE'S CATCHING ONTO SOMETHIN'.
AND IT'S WORKING.
WHETHER OR NOT HE WINS,
HE'S GONNA KEEP GETTING BETTER.
INCREDIBLY SO, TAKUMI WILL
SURPASS US ALL SOME DAY.
- ( tires screeching )
- I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THE MODIFICATIONS ON THE FD.
BUT IT SURE AS HELL
LOOKS SWEET.
- THAT'S THE WAY
KEISUKE LIKES IT.
THE LOOK OF IT IS ONE HUNDRED
PERCENT HIS OWN DESIGN.
- SO HOW'D SHE DO?
- THE INCLINES ARE
STEEPER THAN I EXPECTED.
SO THE BALANCE IS SHIFTING
TOO MUCH TO THE REAR.
- YOU WANT ME TO RAISE HER UP
IN BACK A LITTLE?
- YEAH, I THINK THAT'D
HELP A LOT.
- YOU'RE KEISUKE, THE GUY
DRIVING THE FD, RIGHT?
THAT'S A REAL NICE CAR.
- MMM-HMM.
- YOU GOT THAT BADASS THING
GOIN' ON PRETTY WELL.
BET YOU'RE POPULAR
WITH THE LADY, HUH.
I'M NOT HITTING ON YOU, KID.
IT'S JUST THAT I WAS SOMETHING
OF A LADIES MAN
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER TOO.
GUESS WE CAN
RECOGNIZE OUR OWN.
YOUTH IS THE MOST IRREPLACEABLE
OF COMMODITIES.
WHEN YOU GET TO BE MY AGE AND
YOU START STRAPPING THIS MUCH
DEAD WEIGHT AROUND
YOUR GUT LIKE I HAVE,
WELL, LETS JUST SAY THE BRAS
DON'T COME FLYING OFF THE GIRLS
THE WAY THEY USE TO.
DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED
ON THE AMOUNT OF MONEY
YOU GOTTA SPEND ON 'EM EITHER,
BUT STILL,
THE JOY YOU FEEL
WHEN YOU LAND ONE
IS GREATER THAN ANYTHING YOU
EVER FELT WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
IT'S EVEN BETTER THAN
ANY ONE OF THE HUNDREDS
OF WINS I HAD IN MY DAY.
ANYWAYS, I'M SURE IT'LL ALL COME
INTO FOCUS FOR YOU EVENTUALLY.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR YOU TO SCREW
AROUND WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG.
I GET IT.
SEE YA LATER.
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
I HAD SOMETHING ELSE I CAME OVER
HERE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
JUST A LITTLE IDEA ABOUT THE
BATTLE I WANTED TO TOSS AT YOU.
- YEAH, OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKIN'?
- OH, HOW SHOULD I PUT THIS?
WHEN YOU'RE RACING
A MOUNTAIN PASS,
HAVING BOTH A DOWNHILL AND
AN UPHILL'S PAR FOR THE COURSE.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE TWEAKED
OUT MY CAR SPECIFICALLY
FOR THE UPHILL OR ANYTHING.
I ALWAYS BELIEVED TOTAL BALANCE
IS WHAT MAKES A
TRUE STREET RACER.
SO HERE'S WHAT I'M
PROPOSING TO YOU.
LET'S NOT MAKE OUR BATTLE
JUST AN UPHILL.
I FIGURE WE'RE SKILLED ENOUGH,
SWITCH IT UP,
MAKE IT MORE INTERESTING.
- HOLD ON. YOU WANNA
RACE ME IN A MIXED STAGE,
WITH BOTH UPHILL AND DOWNHILL?
THAT'S WHAT I'M THINKIN', YEAH.
- KICK ASS. THAT MEANS I CAN
SHOW OFF EVERYTHING I GOT,
ESPECIALLY ON THE DOWNHILL.
THAT SOUNDS ALL RIGHT. WE CAN
DO IT JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
I THINK I'LL ENJOY THAT.
- YOU SURE SHOW A
LOT OF PROMISE, BOY.
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
OH, AND ONE MORE THING
BEFORE I GO.
YOU THINK YOU AND I CAN
DO OUR BATTLE FIRST?
- YOU MEAN BEFORE THEY
RUN THE DOWNHILL?
- JUST TO AMP UP THE
EXCITEMENT FOR ME.
I'M GETTING KIND OF IMPATIENT
IN MY OLD AGE.
WAITING FOR THINGS
GETS UNDER MY SKIN.
- THAT WORKS FOR ME TOO.
I'M PRETTY MUCH THE SAME WAY.
- WELL, OKAY.
I DON'T MIND TELLING YOU THAT
I'M GETTING REALLY PUMPED
ABOUT THIS BATTLE.
CATCH YOU LATER.
- HOPE YOU DIDN'T MIND ME MAKING
THE CALL ON THAT ONE, BRO.
JUST DIDN'T SEEM LIKE THERE WAS
ANY REASON TO TELL THE GUY NO.
- NAH, I THINK IT'LL BE FINE.
I'LL ADMIT IT WAS KINDA
UNEXPECTED TURN OF EVENTS,
BUT AFTER MEETING THEM I DOUBT
THEY HAVE ANY ILL INTENT.
AFTER ALL, IT ENDS UP
HELPING US OUT.
IT MAKES THE RACE A LITTLE
MORE ADVANTAGEOUS FOR US
WITHOUT MAKING US LOOK
LIKE A BUNCH OF JERKS.
I GOTTA GIVE THEM CREDIT.
WE HAVEN'T FACED ANYONE YET
THAT OFFERED US THE CHANCE
TO MAKE THE RACE MORE FAIR.
IT'S EASY TO BE GENEROUS WHEN
YOU KNOW YOU'RE THE BEST.
- I'M ALL CHARGED UP. IT'S BEEN
A WHILE SINCE I BEEN ITCHIN'
THIS BAD TO GET
BEHIND THE WHEEL.
- ( car accelerating )
- THAT OLD DUDE, I DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH OF A THREAT HE IS
BUT HE'S GOOD.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
IT'S LIKE THERE'S A WEIGHT
ON MY SHOULDERS,
EVEN MORE THAN USUAL.
WHATEVER IT IS, THIS WILL
STILL BE ONE HELL OF A RACE.
- Keisuke: ( sighs )
I'M BEAT, DUDE.
- PRACTICE WORE
ME OUT, TOO.
- Fumihiro: KEISUKE, FUJIWARA.
THERE YOU GUYS ARE.
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
WE BOOKED A LODGE AT THE
BASE OF THE MOUNTAIN
FOR YOU TWO STAY IN.
- YOU WHAT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE BOTH GETTING TO
SLEEP IN A NICE
AIR-CONDITIONED
ROOM FOR A CHANGE.
- YEAH, OKAY.
BUT WHY JUST US TWO.
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE THE DRIVERS.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA WIN
OR LOSE IT FOR ALL OF US.
- NAH. I DON'T NEED
A ROOM, REALLY.
I'LL JUST SLEEP IN THE BACK
OF MY CAR LIKE I USUALLY DO.
RYOSUKE, WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
MY PLACE INSTEAD?
- I'VE NEVER HAD TO
PULL RANK BEFORE,
BUT YOU CAN CONSIDER THIS
A DIRECT ORDER
FROM YOUR TEAM LEADER.
IT'S FAR TOO HOT THIS
TIME OF YEAR FOR YOU
TO BE SLEEPING IN YOUR CAR.
IT COULD AFFECT YOUR DRIVING.
IT'S CRITICALLY
IMPORTANT THAT YOU DON'T FEEL
ANY FATIGUE TONIGHT.
YOU NEED TO KEEP YOUR
CONCENTRATION
AS HIGH AS POSSIBLE.
- BASICALLY, IT'S IMPORTANT FOR
YOU TWO TO GET BEAUTY REST
FOR THE SAKE OF THE TEAM.
I'LL RUN YOU DOWN TO THE LODGE.
GO GRAB YOUR THINGS AND
HOP INTO VAN NUMBER ONE.
- FUMIHIRO SAID HE'D
SWING BACK HERE
TO PICK US UP AROUND FOUR.
- THAT GIVE US LONGER TO SLEEP
THAN I EVER GET BACK HOME.
- ( Keisuke grunting )
I ALMOST FEEL BAD FOR
THE OTHER GUYS.
I GOTTA SAY, THOUGH, FEELS
PRETTY DAMN GOOD
TO BE ABLE TO STRETCH
OUT FOR ONCE.
- NO QUESTION ABOUT THAT, MAN.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME SINCE
WE'VE STARTED OUR EXPEDITIONS
WITH D WE'VE HAD ANYTHING
COOL HAPPEN.
- WE COULD USE THE REST.
THIS IS GONNA BE A ROUGH BATTLE.
WORSE THAN YOU MIGHT THINK.
IT'S A SHORT COURSE,
BUT IT'S GOT ALL THESE DETAILS
THAT ARE REAL TOUGH TO NAIL.
- ALL THOSE SLOW
WINDING, CORNERS,
NOT BEING ABLE TO SEE
WHAT'S COMING UP NEXT,
FORGET ABOUT PLANNING.
- AND THE BLACKTOP'S ONE OF
THE BUMPIEST I'VE SEEN.
DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA HOW I CAN
MAKE IT THROUGH THAT SUCKER
IN JUST ONE SHOT.
HE'S ALREADY ASLEEP?
NO WAY!
IT'S LIKE HE DOESN'T EVEN FEEL
THE PRESSURE WE'RE UNDER.
MUST BE NICE.
HE MIGHT COME ACROSS AS NAIVE,
MAYBE A LITTLE DUMB,
BUT THE TRUTH IS
THE GUY'S TOUGH.
I'M THE DELICATE ONE.
- Fumihiro: WHAT IN THE HELL
IS KENTA DOING?
- HE SLATHERED OIL ALL OVER
HIS BODY TO GET A TAN.
- WHAT A FREAKIN' IDIOT.
WHY DOES HE NEED TO GET ANY
DARKER THAN HE ALREADY IS?
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE
CAN STAND TO BE OUT HERE.
I FEEL LIKE I'M ON FIRE.
- PROBABLY CLOSE TO A
THOUSAND DEGREES IN THE CARS.
- IT WAS A SMART IDEA GETTING
KEISUKE AND TAKUMI
TO A COOL ROOM WHERE
THEY COULD RELAX. LUCKY.
- ABSOLUTELY.
ESPECIALLY FOR THIS BATTLE.
THEY GOTTA BE IN THE
BEST SHAPE OF THEIR LIVES,
BOTH PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY.
- RYOSUKE ALREADY HAD THE
WHOLE SHEBANG WORKED OUT
WAY BEFORE WE GOT HERE.
BUT I WOULDN'T EXPECT ANYTHING
LESS OUT OF THE GUY
NOW THAT I THINK OF IT.
- YEAH. NO DOUBT.
- MAN, FUJIWARA SURE IS
TAKING HIS SWEET ASS TIME
LOOKING OVER THE COURSE.
- HE'S BEEN GONE FOR WHAT?
AN HOUR, MAYBE TWO?
- YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AND KEISUKE WAS THERE
AND BACK IN ABOUT
AS LONG AS IT TAKES TO PISS.
- SO ARE YOU PLANNING ON
ACTUALLY RACING TODAY?
- ( laughs )
- HEY, SHUT UP, I GOT MY
OWN STYLE, DOUCHE BAG.
I MAY HAVE BEEN FAST, BUT
I DID EVERYTHING I HAD TO DO.
- WELL, WE'RE ALL
COUNTING ON YOU.
YOU'RE UP FIRST TONIGHT,
WE'D LOVE TO LEAD WITH A WIN.
- I'M READY TO GO TO BAT.
I'VE HAD A GREAT NIGHT SLEEP
IN A COOL PLACE,
SO I FEELIN' LIKE A
MILLION BUCKS.
- BEEN WAITIN' FOR
THIS A LONG TIME, MAN.
IT'S GONNA BE A
MASSIVE BLOWOUT.
- GOOD TO SEE JOUSHIMA AND
HOSHINO STEP OUT OF THE SHADOWS
TO THROW DOWN IN A BATTLE
WITH THESE BADASSES DRIVERS
FROM PROJECT D.
IT'S A ONCE IN A
LIFETIME OPPORTUNITY
TO SEE LEGENDS RACING LEGENDS.
- YOU KNOW I'VE HEARD
A LOT ABOUT D,
BUT HOW GOOD ARE THEY REALLY?
THEY'RE GOING UP AGAINST GUYS
WHO GOT THE WORD GOD
IN THEIR NICK NAMES.
THINK THEY CAN
HOLD UP TO THAT?
- ALL I KNOW IS THAT THEY'RE
NOT YOUR AVERAGE DRIVERS.
BOTH GUYS THEY GOT BEHIND THE
WHEEL ARE LIKE 20 YEARS OLD,
AND THEY BEEN AT THIS A WHILE.
THEY'VE BEEN ALL
OVER NORTHERN KANTOU
AND HAVEN'T LOST ONE
SINGLE RACE YET.
SO I'M GONNA GO OUT ON A LIMB
AND SAY THEY'RE
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
- I TELL YA, THEY BETTER BE THE
BEST IN THE FREAKIN' REGION.
I DIDN'T COME ALL
THE WAY UP HERE
JUST TO WATCH SOME
KIDS GET BEAT.
- MAN, A LOT OF PEOPLE
TURNED OUT FOR THIS ONE.
- NOT AS MANY AS THERE'D BE
IF D STOPPED POSTING
THE TIME AND LOCATION
OF THEIR RACES.
THEY MUST'VE BEEN GETTIN'
TOO MANY SHOWING UP TO WATCH,
TOO MANY DISTRACTIONS ON THE
ROAD TO HAVE A SAFE BATTLE.
BUT THEY'VE GOT A FAN SITE UP.
THEY LEAK THE INFO IN
JUST ENOUGH TIME
FOR PEOPLE TO MAKE THE RACE.
- HUH? I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
MUST SUCK TO BE POPULAR.
POOR BASTARDS.
- MY GEAR HAND'S STARTIN'
TO TWITCH.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET OUT THERE
AND START TEARIN' THE ROAD UP.
- EASY NOW. WATCH THAT
COCKINESS OF YOURS, BUDDY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT CAN DO.
- KEEP YOUR PANTYHOSE ON.
THE PRIDE OF THE PURPLE SHADOW
IS A POWERFUL THING.
I'M NOT GONNA
LOSE TO SOME KID.
I MAYBE OLD BUT I CAN STILL
TEACH A PUNK A LESSON OR TWO.
- Fumihiro: WE'LL DO THE HILL
CLIMB FIRST, GUYS.
THE PYLON AT THE
TOP OF THE COURSE
IS YOUR TURN AROUND POINT.
ONCE YOU FLIP THAT, COME
BACK DOWN, THAT'S ONE RUN.
AND OF COURSE WE'LL
REPEAT AS NECESSARY.
DOES THAT SOUND OK TO YOU, SIR?
- THAT'S JUST FINE.
AND SINCE WE'RE DOING
A MIXED STAGE
OF BOTH UPHILL AND DOWNHILL,
YOU FELLAS HAVE ANY
OBJECTIONS TO ME
TAKING THE LEAD ON
THE FIRST RUN?
- NO, NO OBJECTIONS
AT ALL. COOL.
- ALL RIGHT. LET'S GET ROLLING.
AND IN CASE YOU FORGOT,
I'M KOUZOU HOSHINO.
- I'M KEISUKE TAKAHASHI.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪