- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ DOGFIGHT ♪
- ♪ YOU'RE BIG TIME GAMBLER ♪
STRIKE IT, SHAKE IT ♪T
- ( tires screeching )
- ( car approaching )
- ( stopwatch beeps)
- I THINK I'M FINALLY
STARTING TO GET
WHAT YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT, DUDE.
THAT LITTLE CAR IS A HELL OF
A LOT MEANER THAN SHE LOOKS,
THAT'S FOR DAMN SURE. SAKAMOTO'S
TIME ON THIS COURSE IS NUTS.
AND HE'S JUST
SCREWING AROUND.
- IT'S LIKE I SAID,
OUR ADVANTAGE ISN'T ONE
THEY'LL BE EXPECTING.
- YOU MEAN THE CAR'S WEIGHT?
- PRECISELY.
THE CONCEPT OF USING
A LIGHTWEIGHT VEHICLE
TO ONE'S ADVANTAGE
DOESN'T SEEM TO HAVE
OCCURRED TO OUR OPPONENTS.
BUT ON A DOWNHILL RUN
LIKE THIS ONE,
JUST SUCH A CAR CAN GIVE US
EXACTLY THE EDGE WE NEED.
COUPLED WITH THE FACT
WE'LL BE RACING THESE GUYS
ON ONE OF THE TIGHT COURSES
SAITAMA IS INFAMOUS FOR.
AND PROJECT D'S
EIGHT-SIX IS TOAST.
BESTED BY A CAPPUCCINO.
- ( tires screeching )
- OUR BOY'S CERTAINLY
A HARDCORE RALLYIST.
THERE AREN'T MANY
DRIVERS LEFT OUT THERE
WHO WOULD DARE TAKE A CORNER
AT SPEEDS LIKE HE DOES, LET
ALONE IN A VEHICLE SO COMPACT.
THE WHEELBASE IS SHORT.
IT SPINS OUT MUCH EASIER.
- Wataru: I WARNED YOU
HE WAS CRAZY.
MAKES NO DIFFERENCE TO HIM
WHAT KIND OF RIDE
HE'S BEHIND THE WHEEL OF.
IF HE WANTS IT TO DRIFT,
THEN BY GOD THE DAMN
THING'S GOING TO DRIFT.
IT'S HOW HE WORKS OUT
WHAT LIMITATIONS A NEW CAR HAS.
IT'S CRAZY, BUT IT WORKS.
IN A WAY, HE AND
THE EIGHT-SIX'S DRIVER
ARE LIKE TWO OF A KIND.
WOW, JUST THINKING ABOUT IT,
IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME THE
EIGHT-SIX'S WINNING STREAK
CAME TO AN END,
AND WHO BETTER TO WITNESS IT
IN PERSON THAN US?
- I COULDN'T AGREE
WITH YOU MORE.
AND WHO BETTER TO BRING
PROJECT D TO ITS KNEES
THAN THE NORTHERN
SAITAMA ALLIANCE?
- ALL FINISHED.
- NICE JOB.
I GOT TO SAY, IT'S AMAZING
HOW MUCH THIS BABY'S CHANGED
SINCE THE TWO OF US
HAVE BEEN SHARING IT.
I'M WILLING TO BET THERE ARE AS
MANY MODIFICATIONS I CAN'T SEE.
- YOU MIGHT BE
RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
THE HEADLIGHTS ARE A LOT
LIGHTER THAN THEY USE TO BE.
SO THAT'S DIFFERENT.
- SO I'M GUESSING IT'S SAFE
TO ASSUME THAT YOU'VE GONE
FROM HOBBY TO FULL-BLOWN
OBSESSION AT THIS POINT.
TAKUMI?
- THE EIGHT-SIX IS YOURS
FROM NOW ON.
- WHAT?
YOU'RE AN ADULT NOW, A LITTLE
TOO OLD TO BE SHARING A RIDE
WITH YOUR DECREPIT FATHER,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
YOU'RE NOT JUST GIVING ME
THE EIGHT-SIX, ARE YOU?
- HERE I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HAPPY.
- WELL, OF COURSE I AM.
I'M THRILLED. BUT I MEAN...
WHAT'RE YOU GOING TO TOOL
AROUND IN, A WHEEL CHAIR?
- NOT QUITE, I'M IN THE PROCESS
OF BUYING A USED CAR.
AN OLDIE, BUT A GOODIE.
- SO WHAT KIND OF OLDIE
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU KNOW, MORE PRACTICAL,
EASIER TO DRIVE.
ONE BETTER SUITED TO MY AGE.
- AN OLDIE BUT A GOODIE
THEN, HUH?
THE HELL'S GOTTEN INTO HIM?
- GO AHEAD AND REGISTER
THE EIGHT-SIX IN YOUR NAME.
YOU START PAYING TAXES
ON HER NEXT YEAR.
- ALL RIGHT.
- WELL, OF COURSE
THAT'S TAKING A LEAP OF FAITH
AND ASSUMING SHE'LL STILL BE
RUNNING NEXT YEAR.
- COME ON, WHY WOULD YOU
EVEN SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
YOU BET YOUR ASS
SHE'LL BE RUNNING.
BELIEVE ME, SHE'LL RUN FOREVER
IF I HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY ABOUT IT.
I'M IN LOVE WITH THIS CAR.
- WELL, THEN I'M HAPPY
FOR YOU BOTH.
YOU CAN TAKE CARE OF HER
ON YOUR OWN FROM NOW ON, TOO.
- Fumihiro: THE COURSE
WE'RE SCOUTING OUT TODAY
IS ANOTHER TIGHT ONE.
AND IF THAT WEREN'T ENOUGH,
APPARENTLY IT'S GOT STORM DRAINS
- RUNNING ACROSS
BOTH SIDES OF THE ROAD.
- THAT'S WHAT I HEAR.
- YOU'D THINK THAT AS BIG
AS SAITAMA IS
THERE WOULD BE AT LEAST ONE
COURSE THAT WASN'T A DEATH TRAP.
- NO KIDDING.
- OH, AND BY THE WAY, KEISUKE,
IT'S REALLY NONE OF MY
BUSINESS OR ANYTHING, BUT...
- WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
- WELL, IT'S JUST THAT GIRL
STRIKES ME AS A GREAT CATCH.
SHE SEEMED NICE, TOO.
I MEAN, YOU DO HAVE TO ADMIT,
IT WAS REALLY SWEET OF HER TO
COME ALL THE WAY OUT TO AKAGI.
WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE?
- THAT'S NOT IT.
YEAH, SHE'S COOL,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER WHETHER
I LIKE HER OR NOT.
WHAT I HAVE TO DO IS
FOCUS ON PROJECT D.
I WAS STRAIGHT WITH HER.
SHE KNOWS THE LAST THING I
NEED TO WORRY ABOUT NOW
IS SOME CHICK.
- I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND
ME SAYING SO,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK YOU
MIGHT BE A LITTLE TOO FOCUSED
ON PROJECT D?
YOU CAN'T JUST EAT, SLEEP
AND BREATHE IT 24/7.
THINK OF IT LIKE DRIVING.
SOMETIMES YOU PICK UP SPEED
BY ACTUALLY LETTING OFF THE
ACCELERATOR A LITTLE,
INSTEAD OF JUST MASHING PEDAL
TO FLOORBOARD
AND WHITE-KNUCKLING
THE STEERING WHEEL, I MEAN.
( laughs ) LOOK AT ME,
TRYING TO GIVE YOU ROMANTIC
ADVICE BY DRESSING IT UP
IN SOME HALF-BAKED
RACING METAPHOR.
WHO THE HELL
DO I THINK I AM?
FOR THE RECORD, THOUGH,
I DON'T THINK IT'S HEALTHY
FOR ANYONE TO BE
SO SINGLE-MINDED.
HEY, JUST THINK OF ALL THE GOOD
TIMES YOU'RE MISSING OUT ON.
THAT'S ALL I'M REALLY
TRYING TO SAY HERE.
BESIDES, IT DOESN'T TAKE
A GENIUS TO FIGURE OUT
THAT GIRL'S ALL THAT'S BEEN
ON YOUR MIND LATELY.
COME ON, MAN,
YOU CAN'T THINK THE SAME THING'S
GONNA HAPPEN WITH HER
THAT HAPPENED WITH THE LAST GIRL
YOU WENT OUT WITH.
THIS ONE GETS IT.
SHE'S A RACER.
- THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
LET'S JUST CHANGE THE DAMN
SUBJECT, ALL RIGHT, MAN?
- Kyoko: NORTHERN
SAITAMA ALLIANCE?
- YEAH. A BUNCH OF US
ARE TRYING TO GET ORGANIZED
TO HEDGE OUR BETS
AGAINST PROJECT D.
NONE OF US STAND A CHANCE OF
BEATING THOSE GUYS INDIVIDUALLY.
SCRAPING TOGETHER LIKE THIS
IS OUR BEST OPTION,
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH CHOICE.
SO, BASICALLY, WE'RE PUTTING
TOGETHER A NEW TEAM.
IT'LL TEMPORARILY BE
HEADED BY NOBUHIKO.
- IS THAT RIGHT?
- BUT WHAT WE NEED MORE THAN
ANYTHING RIGHT NOW IS MONEY.
SO WE'RE ALL CHIPPING IN, YOU
KNOW, WHATEVER WE'RE ABLE TO.
WOULD YOU CARE TO MAYBE
MAKE A LITTLE DONATION YOURSELF?
- YEAH, OKAY, I CAN CHIP IN.
WHAT, DO YOU THINK FIVE THOUSAND
YEN WOULD BE ENOUGH?
- HEY, KYOKO. GOT A SEC?
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- ABOUT WHAT?
- YOU CHIPPING IN
TO HELP BEAT PROJECT D.
LOOK, THERE'S NOT REALLY AN EASY
WAY FOR ME TO ASK YOU THIS
SO I'LL JUST COME
RIGHT OUT WITH IT.
WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU REALLY ON, KYOKO?
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU MEAN?
- I'M TALKING ABOUT
IN YOUR HEART.
WHO ARE YOU
ACTUALLY ROOTING FOR?
NOBUHIKO AND THE GUYS
ARE COLLECTING FUNDS
'CAUSE THEY WANT TO
PUT A STOP TO PROJECT D.
IF YOU'RE NOT DOWN WITH IT,
DON'T CHIP IN.
LOOK, I'M NOT SAYING THIS
TO BE AN ASSHOLE.
I MEAN, YOU GET ME, RIGHT?
- MMM-HMM.
- THERE'S ONE MORE THING
I THINK YOU OUGHT TO KNOW.
THE TAKAHASHI
BROTHERS ARE THE SONS
OF A BIG-TIME HOSPITAL
ADMINISTRATOR,
THEIR FAMILY IS TOTALLY
FREAKING LOADED.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHY AM I ALWAYS THE LAST ONE
TO KNOW THIS STUFF?
- THEY'RE BOTH GOOD LOOKING GUYS
WITH MONEY TO BURN,
THOSE DUDES ARE IN A LEAGUE
OF THEIR OWN.
I'M NOT SAYING IT'S IMPOSSIBLE,
I'M JUST SAYING.
- LIKE HE'D NEVER NOTICE ME?
- NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
IT'S JUST...
I MEAN THEY'RE BOTH
REALLY POPULAR.
SO, YOU'D JUST BE
SETTING YOURSELF UP
FOR HEARTACHE. YOU KNOW THAT.
LOOK, IT'S THE TRUTH, ALL RIGHT.
I WAS ONLY TRYING TO HELP OUT.
- I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- ( tires screeching )
- DAMN. LOOKS TO ME LIKE HE'S
COMING RIGHT ALONG, HUH?
- YOU KNOW, THERE ARE
PURISTS OUT THERE
WHO WOULD CALL THIS CHEATING,
BUT I REALLY COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHAT THEY THINK
ABOUT OUR TACTICS.
SO LONG AS PROJECT D LOSES.
- Itsuki: YOU'RE CHANGING THE
REGISTRATION ON THE EIGHT-SIX?
SO WHAT'S YOUR OLD MAN PLANNING
ON TEARING AROUND TOWN IN?
- HE SAID HE'S ABOUT
TO BUY SOMETHING USED.
- USED? THAT'S TERRIBLE!
- I DON'T THINK HE WANTED TO
TELL ME WHAT IT IS YET.
FROM THE WAY HE WAS CARRYING
ON ABOUT HIS AGE
YOU'D THINK IT WAS A VAN
OR STATION WAGON
OR SOME PIECE
OF CRAP HATCHBACK.
- OH, YOU'RE KILLING ME.
DON'T GIVE ME
A VISUAL LIKE THAT.
THAT MAN WAS ONCE THE RACING
PRIDE OF THIS WHOLE REGION.
HE CAN'T LET HIMSELF BE SEEN
BEHIND THE WHEEL OF A VAN.
- HE HAS GOTTEN OLD, DUDE.
IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S EVER GOING
TO START RACING AGAIN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW GOOD YOU ARE,
IN THE END A GUY CAN ONLY
LIVE UP TO HIS OWN LEGEND
FOR SO LONG, YOU KNOW?
- ( Bunta sneezing )
- I GUESS I BETTER GET GOING.
I'M GONNA BE LATE FOR OUR
MEETING TONIGHT.
I'LL CATCH UP
WITH YOU LATER, MAN.
- DON'T FORGET WHO YOU'RE
REPRESENTING OUT THERE, BUDDY.
AND GOOD LUCK. ME AND THE GUYS
ARE GONNA BE THERE TOMORROW
TO CHEER YOU ON.
- Ryosuke: I'LL BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
THE WAY THINGS ARE GOING,
I THINK THIS RACE MIGHT SHAPE UP
TO BE THE BIGGEST CHALLENGE
TAKUMI'S EVER FACED.
- YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
CONSIDERING THE KIND OF DRIVERS
HE'S ALREADY GONE UP AGAINST,
I'D BE SURPRISED IF HE
FOUND ANYTHING A CHALLENGE.
I MEAN, WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT THE SAME TAKUMI
WHO DUSTED A PROFESSIONAL,
AREN'T WE?
- TOMORROW NIGHT'S RACE
WILL MAKE THAT ONE
LOOK LIKE A WALK IN THE
PARK, MOST LIKELY.
- HUH? WHAT COULD BE TOUGHER
THAN RACING A PROFESSIONAL?
- TAKE MY WORD FOR IT,
YOUR TOUGHEST OPPONENT ISN'T
ALWAYS THE GUY YOU'RE RACING.
- SORRY, MAN.
I DON'T GET YOUR MEANING.
- YOU WILL SOON ENOUGH.
I'M GONNA TAKE A LITTLE NAP.
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND
WAKING ME UP WHEN WE GET THERE,
I'D APPRECIATE IT.
- YEAH, NOT A PROBLEM.
"NOT THE GUY YOU'RE RACING"?
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
- LOOK WHO IT IS.
- WELL, HIYA, FELLAS. WE WERE
WONDERING WHEN YOU'D SHOW UP.
OH, COME ON,
YOU REMEMBER ME, DON'T YOU?
- OF COURSE, HOW COULD I FORGET?
- DON'T WORRY. YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GO UP AGAINST ME IN THIS RACE.
I'M HERE FOR MORAL SUPPORT.
- HOLD ON. AREN'T YOU...
- YES. SORRY FOR ALL
THE FAMILIAR FACES.
I'M ONLY HERE
TO SET EVERYTHING UP.
WE'VE BROKEN IN THE COURSE
FOR YOU, SO TO SPEAK.
BY ALL MEANS,
PRACTICE AS LONG AS YOU NEED.
- THANK YOU.
- SEE YOU AROUND.
- LOT OF HUMIDITY IN THE AIR.
THAT MEANS MORE
THAN A GOOD CHANCE
FOR RAIN TOMORROW NIGHT.
- NOT EXACTLY
AN IDEAL SITUATION.
- WELL, IT SHOULDN'T
BE A PROBLEM
ONCE YOU'VE GOT THE DETAILS
OF THIS COURSE
ETCHED INTO YOUR BRAIN.
STAY FOCUSED. I WANT FIFTY
RUNS BEFORE DAYBREAK.
- RIGHT.
- HELL, YEAH.
- ( engine revving )
- IT LOOKS LIKE
EVERYTHING CHECKS OUT.
READY WHEN YOU ARE, DUDE.
- OKAY, MAN. LET HER RIP.
- I WONDER WHERE KYOKO IS?
- ( tires screeching )
- THE PROJECT D GUYS
WILL HAVE STARTED
THEIR PRACTICE RUNS BY NOW.
I REALLY WANT TO GO
SEE THEM, BUT...
I DON'T DARE.
I FEEL LIKE THE BAT FROM
THE STUPID AESOP'S FABLE
MOM USED TO READ ME.
NOT A BIRD. NOT A BEAST,
JUST LEFT OUT.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS IT GONNA RAIN TOMORROW?
- PROBABLY, YES, BUT FOR
OUR INTENTS AND PURPOSES,
THE BAD WEATHER MAY
JUST TURN OUT THE BE
SAKAMOTO'S ACE IN THE HOLE.
THE MORE WET AND TREACHEROUS
THE ROAD GETS,
THE MORE ADVANTAGEOUS
THAT VEHICLE'S LIGHT WEIGHT
BECOMES FOR HIM IN THE RACE.
- YEAH, BUT, IF IT RAINS
WON'T THEY JUST CANCEL?
I MEAN, WE CAN'T EXPECT
THEM TO RISK THEIR NECKS
FOR A RACE LIKE THIS.
- CANCEL? HARDLY.
BOTH CARS ARE FD'S, AFTER ALL,
AND THEY'LL BE DRIVING
UNDER THE SAME CONDITIONS.
BESIDES, THEY'RE NOT THE TYPE
TO BACK DOWN
BECAUSE OF A LITTLE RAIN.
THE SITUATION'S NEARLY PERFECT.
YOU KNOW, IF I WERE
THE SUPERSTITIOUS TYPE,
I'D THINK LADY LUCK
HAD A LITTLE CRUSH ON US.
ONE MIGHT SAY OUR STRATEGY
AGAINST THE D BOYS
IS WATERTIGHT.
- ( upbeat song playing )
- GIVE HER A LITTLE GAS.
ONLY TEN LITERS.
- RIGHT.
- KEISUKE.
ONCE YOU'RE USED TO IT,
DRIVE THE COURSE WITH
JUST YOUR FOG LIGHTS ON.
TRY TO MAKE THE RUN
WITHOUT HIGH BEAMS.
VISIBILITY WILL WORSEN
IF IT STARTS TO POUR.
YOU NEED TO BE ABLE TO DRIVE
THIS COURSE FROM MEMORY,
NOT BASED ON WHAT YOU WON'T
BE ABLE TO SEE TOMORROW NIGHT.
- AS A PRECAUTION AGAINST THE
RAIN, HUH? SURE THING, BRO.
I'LL DO THE BEST I CAN.
- ♪ AND YOU'RE SPINNING LIKE
YOU'RE NEVER STOPPING ♪
♪ YOU NEVER DID BEFORE ♪
♪ SPINNING MORE ♪
♪ STEEL BLADE ♪
♪ YOU'RE TURNING FAST,
A COUNTDOWN TO THE BLAST ♪
♪ AND I'M HITTING LIKE
I'LL NEVER LOSE IT ♪
♪ ONE PULLING AND I WON ♪
♪ NUMBER ONE ♪
- DAMN IT. WHY CAN'T I
GET HIM OUT OF MY HEAD?
MY BABY'S FD?
OH, WHAT THE HELL.
NO ONE'S LOOKING.
( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN THERE?
- THE HELL ARE YOU DOING
OUT HERE?
LAST TIME I CHECKED
THIS WAS MY CAR.
- SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN TO
OVERREACT. YOU JUST STARTLED ME.
BUT SERIOUSLY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO CATCH UP
ON A FEW Z'S, YOU KNOW.
I'VE GOT A BIG RACE
COMING UP TONIGHT.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT! I HEARD!
GOOD LUCK TO YOU AND YOUR
TEAM TONIGHT, I HOPE YOU WIN.
- THANKS, WE'RE GONNA NEED IT.
I'VE BARELY SLEPT A WINK.
IT'S TOO DAMN BRIGHT OUT HERE,
PLUS I'M SO HUNGRY RIGHT NOW
I THINK I COULD
EAT A FREAKING HORSE.
DO YOU WANT TO
GRAB A BITE OR SOMETHING?
- SO, PLACES LIKE THIS,
DO YOU LIKE THEM?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "LIKE THIS"?
- FAMILY RESTAURANTS.
- HUH?
OH, YEAH,
I LOVE THIS KIND OF FOOD.
STREET RACERS NEED A LOT
OF CARBS TO STAY SHARP.
- I GUESS THAT MAKES
A LOT OF SENSE.
FOR A RICH KID WHOSE DAD
RUNS A MAJOR HOSPITAL,
MY DARLING SURE IS
DOWN TO EARTH. THANK GOD!
- HEY, KEISUKE'S GONE. WHERE
DO YOU THINK HE RAN OFF TO?
- HE PROBABLY JUST WENT FOR A
BITE TO EAT OR SOMETHING,
HE'LL BE BACK BEFORE LONG.
- SO WHAT DID HE DO? HIKE?
- WELL, WHY WOULDN'T HE?
I SAY WE FOLLOW HIS LEAD.
- AW, MAN THAT SMELLS GOOD.
I BET WHEN THE WEATHER'S NICE
LIKE THIS,
THIS PLACE IS PERFECT
FOR HIKING.
HEY, PASS ME SOME TEA,
WOULD YOU?
- Kenta: SURE.
- THANKS.
- YOU GET ANY SHUT-EYE?
- YEAH, SOME.
ABOUT THREE HOURS WORTH.
- GET A FEW MORE
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
YOU'LL NEED YOUR ENERGY
FOR THE RACE TONIGHT.
EVEN IF YOU CAN'T SLEEP,
JUST RELAXING WITH YOUR EYES
CLOSED OUGHT TO DO THE TRICK.
- YEAH. SURE THING.
I THINK I'D LIKE TO GET
A FEW MORE PRACTICE RUNS IN
BEFORE I DO, THOUGH.
I WANT TO DOUBLE-CHECK THE
PLACES WHERE PUDDLES MIGHT FORM
WHILE THERE'S STILL
ENOUGH LIGHT.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
- THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
THE WEATHER'S HELD SO FAR,
BUT I DON'T LIKE THE LOOK
OF THOSE CLOUDS.
- Kyoko: YOU ALWAYS
SLEEP IN YOUR CAR
WHEN PROJECT D'S
OUT IN THE FIELD?
- WELL, MOST OF THE TIME, YEAH.
NOT REALLY THE BEST WAY
TO DO IT, THOUGH, I'LL ADMIT.
THOSE BUCKET SEATS ARE ABSOLUTE
HELL ON THE LOWER BACK.
- YOU POOR THING.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GET A ROOM
AT A HOTEL OR SOMETHING?
- THE DRIVING-ALL-NIGHT,
SLEEPING-ALL-DAY THING
DOESN'T MAKE US LOOK
ALL THAT GREAT.
SO NO REPUTABLE HOTEL WANTS
ANYTHING TO DO WITH OUR CROWD.
- OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DIDN'T THINK OF THAT.
- ( sighing ) NOW THAT
I'VE STUFFED MYSELF,
I'M GETTING KINDA SLEEPY.
MIND IF WE START
HEADING BACK?
- ( rain pattering )
- LOOKS LIKE
IT'S STARTING TO RAIN.
OH, GOD. WHAT DO I DO?
HE'S ASLEEP!
I'LL SLOW DOWN A LITTLE SO THE
RIDE DOESN'T JAR HIM AWAKE.
POOR BABY. HE'S WORN OUT.
IF TIME FROZE LIKE THIS,
IN THIS MOMENT,
I'D BE THE HAPPIEST GIRL ALIVE.
YOU LISTENING UP THERE, BIG GUY?
IF YOU STOPPED TIME RIGHT NOW,
I'D OWE YOU ONE.
- JUST PERFECT.
THIS RAIN IS SOME BULLSHIT.
GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
ACCEPT IT AND DEAL, RIGHT?
- WHY WOULD ANYONE RACE
IN A DOWNPOUR LIKE THIS?
I THINK YOU GUYS HAVE FINALLY
LOST YOUR MINDS, BRO.
- THIS ISN'T GOING TO LET UP
ANY TIME SOON.
- GUESS NOT. WHICH IS SURE TO
MAKE TONIGHT'S RACE INTERESTING.
- HEY, YOU DON'T THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO CANCEL IT, DO YOU?
- WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
START CLOSING UP SHOP.
WE'RE HEADING OUT.
- AYE AYE, SIR!
- WHAT THE HELL? OH, CRAP!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I FELL ASLEEP!
HEY, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT TIME IT IS?
- IT'S ABOUT SIX O'CLOCK.
- SON OF A BITCH,
I'M GONNA BE LATE!
I'M REAL SORRY,
THIS ISN'T LIKE ME.
I'M USUALLY NOT ABLE
TO SLEEP IN A CAR
FOR MORE THAN TWO
OR THREE HOURS.
IT'S PROBABLY A BAD TIME
TO ASK NOW,
BUT IS IT OKAY THAT YOU SPENT
YOUR ENTIRE AFTERNOON WITH ME?
I MEAN, NO ONE WAS EXPECTING YOU
OR ANYTHING, WERE THEY?
- OH, NO, I HAD NOTHING ELSE
PLANNED TODAY ANYWAY.
IT'S TOTALLY ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'LL BE MISSED.
- YOU'RE MESSING WITH ME, RIGHT?
I HATE TO BAIL ON YOU
LIKE THIS, BUT...
MAN, I HOPE THERE'S STILL ENOUGH
TIME FOR ME TO TUNE THE FD.
- ( engine starting )
- SERIOUSLY. THANK YOU.
- HEY! THEY'RE HERE!
IS THAT A CAPPUCCINO?
- SO, HEY, RYOSUKE,
I'VE BEEN THINKING OVER
WHAT WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT LAST NIGHT,
AND I THINK I FINALLY GET IT.
TAKUMI HASN'T FACED A CHALLENGE
LIKE THIS. NOT EVER.
MAN, THIS ISN'T GOOD.
THESE GUYS HAVE REALLY GOT US
BY THE BALLS, DON'T THEY?
THE BRAINS BEHIND
THIS OUTFIT IS SMARTER
THAN I GAVE HIM CREDIT FOR.
- Nobuhiko: LET'S GET
THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD!
- ( engines revving )
- STARTING IN FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE...
GO!
- SON OF A BITCH!
THIS GUY IS FAST!
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ WHO YOU WANT TO BE
WHO YOU WANT TO BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANT TO SEE
WHAT YOU WANT TO SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
♪ BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
♪ STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANT
TO BREAK ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANT TO BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANT
TO BREAK ♪
♪ BE WHAT YOU WANT TO BE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANT TO BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANT
TO BREAK ♪