- ( theme music playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ( cars vrooming )
- THAT'S PRETTY HIP.
SO YOU'RE WORKING FULL TIME
AT THE STATION THESE DAYS?
- YEAH, THE PAY'S CRAP,
BUT IT'S SUCH A BLAST TO BE
WORKING ALL DAY,
COVERED IN GREASE, FIXING
STUFF UP FOR PEOPLE.
I'M JUST GLAD I GET TO SPEND
ALL DAY AROUND CARS.
- YOU'VE GROWN UP A LOT
THESE PAST FEW YEARS, ITSUKI.
ONCE YOU GOT OUT AROUND PEOPLE,
SOMETHING CHANGED IN YOU.
- COME ON, CUT IT OUT. I HAVEN'T
CHANGED ALL THAT MUCH, HAVE I?
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU? I MEAN, LOOK
AT YOU! TALK ABOUT MATURING.
WHOA.
- THANKS, BUT NO. I'M STILL
THE SAME PERSON I ALWAYS WAS.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
WHAT IS IT, DO I HAVE FOOD
ON MY FACE OR SOMETHING?
OH, GOOD. I DON'T
WANNA LOOK STUPID.
- ( screaming )
YOU'VE GOTTEN TOO
DAMN BEAUTIFUL!
- ( thunderclap )
- I NEED TO STRETCH THIS
INTO AN ENDURANCE RACE.
NO WAY MY STREET STAMINA'LL
LOSE OUT TO YOU, RICH BOY.
- YOU PUT A LOT OF TIME AND
EFFORT INTO THAT SUPERCHARGER.
GETTING THE POWER THAT'S
EASIEST TO USE, I GUESS.
THIS WON'T BE AN EASY WIN.
I DOUBT I'LL BE ABLE TO
SHUT HIM DOWN FAST.
WITH THE RAIN POURING DOWN
LIKE THIS,
LOOKS LIKE THE TIME TRIAL'S
OFF THE DOCKET.
GUESS WE MIGHT AS WELL GO WILD.
LET'S TURN IT OUT!
- I FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
I GOT MY DRIVER'S LICENSE.
- WOW. THAT'S GREAT.
IS IT JUST FOR AUTOMATICS
OR CAN YOU
DRIVE STANDARD, TOO?
- NO. I GOT THE THING
FOR STANDARDS.
IF I FELT UP TO IT, I COULD
EVEN GET BEHIND THE WHEEL
OF MY BROTHER'S LEVIN
AND TEAR IT UP.
NOT THAT HE REALLY ENJOYS
LETTING ME. HE HAS SOME,
BUT THE STEERING ON IT IS KINDA
HEAVY. IT'S A TOUGH MACHINE.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA BUY
YOUR OWN CAR?
- I WOULD, BUT DRIVING SCHOOL
WAS WAY TOO EXPENSIVE,
SO I'M BROKE.
I'LL HAVE TO SAVE UP, WHICH
COULD TAKE A LITTLE WHILE,
THE WAY THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING.
- I FORGOT TO TELL YOU! I PUT
A TURBO IN MY EIGHT-FIVE.
IT ROCKS SO HARD.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
HOW FAST THAT MOTHER IS NOW!
I CAN EVEN KEEP UP
WITH IKETANI.
NO KIDDING.
I'VE GOTTEN THAT GOOD!
- SWEET. YOU'VE FINALLY DONE IT.
YOU'VE JOINED THE RANKS
OF THE TRUE STREET RACERS.
- YEAH, I GUESS I HAVE.
IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN DRIVE
MY CAR SOMETIME.
YOU'D LOVE THE WAY IT HANDLES.
- ( spectators cheering )
- SAY WHAT YOU WANT
ABOUT THESE DUDES,
THIS BATTLE IS
TOTALLY ABOUT CONTROL.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY CAN JUST
GUN IT IN THIS DOWNPOUR.
THEY'LL SPIN OUT.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
AND DON'T FORGET THE SLOWER
THEY'RE ROLLING ON THE COURSE,
THE CRAPPIER THE ADVANTAGE
IS FOR THE FD.
- ♪ MY SHAME ♪
♪ IS TO BE FOREVER WILD ♪
♪ CHANGING AFFECTIONS ♪
- Nobuhiko: GOT IT.
CHECK BACK IN A FEW.
THEY'RE TURNING INTO THE HAIRPIN
AT THE CANYON RIGHT NOW.
AND THE FD'S BREATHING
DOWN HIS NECK.
- THEY'RE JUST NOT GONNA LET US
WALK AWAY WITH AN EASY WIN.
THAT FD IS ROCKET CHARGED, MAN.
- KEEPING UP WITH WATARU'S LEVIN
IN THIS RAIN COULDN'T BE EASY
FOR ANYONE,
EVEN THIS GUY FROM D.
BUT CONSIDER ALL ASPECTS
OF HIS GAME.
WHEN HE RACED KYOKO,
I SAW THE WAY HE MANIPULATED
HIS ACCELERATOR,
AND I WOULDN'T PUT
ANYTHING PAST HIM.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK? THIS
THING MIGHT LAST A WHILE, THEN?
- IT COULD. BUT THE
LONGER IT KEEPS UP,
THE BETTER IT IS FOR WATARU.
- YOU CAN SAY WHAT YOU WILL,
BUT I WAS UP AGAINST AN
S-THIRTEEN TURBO!
IT WAS A DEMON! I MEAN,
THERE WASN'T ONE FAIR THING
ABOUT THAT BATTLE.
( laughing )
- WHAT DOES ITSUKI THINK
HE'S DOIN' WITH HER?
GUY THINKS HE CAN DITCH US
TO LAUGH IT UP WITH
SOME PIECE OF TAIL?
DON'T JUST STAND THERE LIKE
A FENCE POST, TAKUMI,
DO SOMETHING.
- DUDE, WHY ME? YOU'RE THE
ONE WHO'S ACTING ALL PISSED.
- Iketani: JUST LOOK AT THAT
SMIRK. DOESN'T IT BUG YOU?
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THOSE TWO?
- LOOK, I DIDN'T KNOW
WATARU WAS GONNA BE HERE
ANY MORE THAN YOU DID,
SO I DEFINITELY DIDN'T KNOW
HIS SISTER WAS.
- I KNOW. IT'S JUST...
TO HAVE KAZUMI SHOW UP HERE
AT THE SAME TIME, THE SAME PLACE
AS ITSUKI. IT'S...
- Kenji: A HELLUVA COINCIDENCE.
SOAP OPERA WRITERS
COULDN'T DO BETTER.
- IF ITSUKI GETS A GIRL, IT'LL
BE A MONSTER BLOW TO MY EGO.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE IT.
- WHY CAN'T MAKO SHOW UP
OUT HERE TOO! DAMMIT, WHY?!
( sulking ) THIS SUCKS.
- HEY, MAN, I GOT SOMETHIN'
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
YOU GOT A FEW MINUTES?
- Keisuke: NICE JOB
KEEPIN' UP WITH ME.
I KNOW WHAT HE'S
FIGHTING THROUGH.
DRIVING A HIGH-POWERED
TURBO ON A RAINY NIGHT
IS A PAIN IN THE ASS.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT THE PUNK HAS SKILLS.
- Sakamoto: THERE'S JUST ONE
THING I'VE GOTTA ASK YOU.
- YEAH, AND I'M BETTING IT'S
ABOUT THAT LAST STRAIGHTAWAY
BEFORE THE FINISH LINE.
- NO, IT ISN'T THAT.
I'M A RALLY DRIVER.
I LIKE TO DRIVE POINT A TO B.
I REALLY COULDN'T CARE LESS
ABOUT LOOKING COOL,
DRIFTING AROUND CORNERS.
CHASING PEOPLE, WHO PASSES
WHO, IT ALL MEANS NOTHING TO ME.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT STUFF.
IT'S NOT MY STYLE.
WHAT I WANNA KNOW
IS ABOUT YOU.
YOU GOT THIS BIG BAD MOTIVATION,
PUSHES YOU FURTHER
THAN ANYONE,
AND ALL I WANNA KNOW IS
WHERE YOU GET IT?
- ( tires screeching )
- Sakamoto: WHEN
WE WERE RACING,
ONE THING ABOUT YOU
REALLY STOOD OUT.
YOU HAVE A HELL OF A STRONG
WILL IN YOU.
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT, THOUGH,
IN TERMS OF OUR CARS'
TECHNICAL ABILITIES,
MINE HAS YOU BEAT
EVERY DAY OF THE WEEK.
OUR TECHNIQUES, THOUGH,
AREN'T THAT FAR OFF.
THIS IS SO WEIRD, MAN. STANDING
HERE, TALKING TO YOU RIGHT NOW,
YOU SEEM LIKE ANY OTHER DUDE
I'D FIND BEHIND A WHEEL.
THIS MOTIVATION OF YOURS,
NOTHING AFFECTS IT,
NOT EVEN THIS DAMN RAIN.
THAT'S EXACTLY THE KINDA THING
I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT.
ONLY AMATEURS PRETEND
THEY'RE NOT AFRAID OF THE RAIN.
RAIN AND ROADS,
AND DRIVING IN THE STUFF
WHITTLES YOUR CONCENTRATION
DOWN TO ALMOST NOTHING.
TO MAINTAIN CONCENTRATION FOR
AN EXTENDED PERIOD OF TIME,
YOU GOTTA HAVE
THE MENTAL CAPACITY OF A GIANT.
I'M TALKIN' SERIOUS STAMINA,
YOU KNOW?
THAT'S WHAT I MEAN WHEN I
TALK ABOUT YOUR MOTIVATION.
AND THAT STRONG WILL OF YOURS?
THAT'S THE KIND OF THING I
RESPECT IN A DRIVER.
I'VE DRIVEN WITH A LOT OF GUYS
AND I CAN TELL BY NOW
THAT THIS KIND OF MOTIVATION
DOESN'T JUST POP UP
WITHOUT SOMETHING
PULLING IT THROUGH.
FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
YOU DRIVE LIKE A PROFESSIONAL.
- A PROFESSIONAL?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
- LISTEN UP! WE'RE STARTING
THE SECOND ROUND!
STARTING IN FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO...
- THIS RUN'S GONNA BE HIS LAST.
- YEAH!
- Fumihiro: GO!
- ( cars revving )
- Nobuhiko: THIS COULD BE
INTERESTING,
BUT I'M CONCERNED ABOUT
THIS SECOND RUN.
KEEPING UP WITH THAT FD COULD
GET PRETTY DANGEROUS FOR HIM.
- I HOPE HE DOESN'T
HURT HIMSELF OUT THERE.
- I'M JUST WORRIED, IS ALL.
I KNOW HE CAN KEEP UP OUT THERE.
THIS ROUTE'S SIMILAR TO HIS
HOME COURSE, IN A LOT OF WAYS.
DRIVES THESE KINDS OF
ROADS EVERYDAY.
- HE'S DOIN' GOOD.
THIS RAIN'S GOTTA BEEN GRATING
ON A ROTARY TURBO LIKE HIS.
'CAUSE WITH A CAR LIKE THAT FD,
IF YOU'RE ROLLIN'
ON THIS SLICK A SURFACE,
YOU CAN'T POP
THAT ACCELERATOR TOO MUCH.
HE'S USING THE HALF-THROTTLE.
THAT'S A HIGH-LEVEL TECHNIQUE.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
MY PLAN'S STILL IN FULL EFFECT.
IN THE ENDURANCE RACE,
THE CAR THAT'S HARD TO HANDLE
WEARS DOWN IT'S DRIVER.
THAT'S WHAT WE GOT HERE.
AND THE SECOND THAT BOY
MAKES A MISTAKE,
I MAKE MY MOVE.
- YEAH, I KNOW, I HEAR YA.
BUT I DON'T REALLY UNDERSTAND
ANY OF THIS EITHER.
I ALWAYS WANT TO GET BETTER.
IT'S WHO I AM.
BUT YOU SAY
THE WORD 'PROFESSIONAL'.
IT JUST SEEMS LIKE
THE OTHER MEMBERS OF D
ARE A LOT BETTER CANDIDATES.
I PRACTICE. I SHOW UP ON TIME.
I DRIVE THE BEST THAT I CAN,
AND I TRY TO NOT DRAG THE TEAM
DOWN. THAT'S ME.
- YEAH, THAT'S ME, TOO.
IT MUST BE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH YOUR ENVIRONMENT, THEN.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
- I'M NINETEEN.
- YOU'RE NINETEEN YEARS OLD?
MAN, I JUST TURNED 26 THIS YEAR.
I SWEAR, IF I HAD YOUR TECHNIQUE
WHEN I WAS NINETEEN,
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT I WOULD'VE ACCOMPLISHED.
I'D BE A DIFFERENT MAN WITH
A WAY DIFFERENT LIFE, RIGHT NOW,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
I ENVY YOU, DUDE.
YOU'VE GOT EVERYTHING
GOING FOR YOU.
YOU CAN ALWAYS GET FASTER
AS LONG AS YOU GO FOR IT.
LATELY, I'VE BEEN IN SOMETHING.
I GUESS YOU COULD
CALL IT A FUNK.
I THOUGHT I'D PICK AT
YOUR BRAIN SOME,
SEE IF YOU COULD DROP
ME A FEW HINTS.
IT WAS WORTHd A SHOT.
SORRY IF I BOTHERED YOU.
- MOTIVATION, HUH? ALL THIS TIME
I'VE BEEN DRIVING,
I NEVER STOPPED TO CONSIDER
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
WHEN I'M WITH PROJECT D, I JUST
FEEL MOTIVATED, NATURALLY.
MUST BE THE ENVIRONMENT,
LIKE HE SAID.
GUESS I'M LUCKY LIKE THAT.
AND I JUST STRAIGHT UP
LIKE THIS CAR.
THAT'S WHY THE STRONGEST FEELING
I HAVE RIGHT NOW,
THE ONE THAT DROWNS OUT
ALL THE OTHERS
IS THAT I DO NOT WANT TO
LOSE TO KEISUKE!
- YEP, HE'S KEEPING UP.
NOT LIKE I CAN DO ANYTHING.
THE ENGINE'S OVERCOMPENSATING
FOR THE RAIN
AND SUCKIN' HALF THE POWER OUT,
SLIDING ME ALL OVER THE ROAD.
THE FD NEEDS A HIGHER SPEED
BATTLE TO SHOW ITS TRUE COLORS.
NOT LIKE THIS.
USED TO BE, I WOULD'VE POPPED
UNDER THE PRESSURE,
BUT WITH ALL THAT ACCELERATOR
TRAINING I'VE BEEN GETTING IN,
IT'S HELPING.
I'M CALMER. I JUST HAVE
TO STAY PATIENT.
WAIT FOR MY CHANCE IS GOING
TO SHOW ITSELF.
TAKUMI WON.
SO I'M GONNA WIN, TOO!
- Fumihiro: THE RACE IS AT
A STALEMATE, ISN'T IT?
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR KEISUKE
THAT THE BATTLE'S GONE ON
FOR AS LONG AS IT HAS.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE MECHANICS OF THE CAR
OR THE BAD DRIVING CONDITIONS.
THEY DON'T MATTER TONIGHT.
- SO YOU THINK THIS IS
A RACE OF SKILL SETS?
DRIVER VERSUS DRIVER?
EACH ONE WAITING TO SEE IF
THE OTHER'S CONCENTRATION
WILL GO FIRST?
- IT'S ALL ABOUT HOW LONG
KEISUKE'S CONCENTRATION
WILL LAST.
- YOU SOUND ALMOST HAPPY
ABOUT THAT.
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
BUT, THERE'S NOT A BETTER
OPPORTUNITY IN THE WORLD
FOR HIM TO MASTER HIS CURRENT
TOPIC THAN HERE, TONIGHT.
I HOPE HE GIVES IT EVERYTHING
IN HIS ARSENAL.
- YEAH, YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
- IF YOU CAN'T USE
YOUR TECHNIQUE TO WIN
IN A HIGH PRESSURE SITUATION,
THEN THERE'S NO POINT TO IT.
- YOU DON'T THINK THAT MAYBE
YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE EXTRA HARD
ON YOUR BROTHER SOMETIMES?
- JACKASS IS STILL ON ME.
THAT SUPERCHARGER
IS A GOOD IDEA.
I MEAN, EVEN THOUGH THEY BOTH
GOTTA USE THE AIR PRESSURE
TO MOVE THE TURBINES,
THE SUPERCHARGER CAN PULL POWER
RIGHT FROM THE CRANKSHAFT.
IT'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
- BEST THING ABOUT
THIS SUPERCHARGER
IS YOU CAN GET THE
POWER LINEARLY
WHILE YOU'RE STILL INCREASING
ENGINE ROTATION.
TURBO CHARGERS HAVE TURBO LAG.
SUPERCHARGERS DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
SURE, TURBOS MAYBE BE ABLE
TO KICK OUT A LITTLE MORE POWER,
BUT WITH THIS BABY, I GET A
CONSISTENT BOOST OF ENERGY
AS LONG AS I KEEP MY
FOOT PRESSED DOWN
ON THAT ACCELERATOR.
GET OUT ON A WINDING ROAD
WITH A LOW AVERAGE SPEED
AND THE SUPERCHARGER ABSOLUTELY
HAS THE UPPER HAND
OVER THE TURBO!
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
- Kenji: CRAZY. I CAN'T
BELIEVE THEY'RE GOING
INTO THE THIRD RUN.
THIS IS TAKING FOREVER.
I FIGURED THIS WOULD BE
A SLAM-DUNK.
IT MUST MEAN THAT
THE TWO OF THEM
ARE PRETTY CLOSE IN SKILL LEVEL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- Takumi: NAH, IT'S THE RAIN.
BECAUSE OF THAT, THE CAR THAT'S
CHASING HAS AN EASIER TIME
MATCHING HIS PACE TO THE CAR
THAT'S OUT IN FRONT.
IF THEY WERE TO
MAKE SEPARATE RUNS,
THEIR TIMES WOULD DEPEND ON
HOW CAUTIOUS EACH DRIVER IS.
BUT TOGETHER,
UNDER THESE CONDITIONS,
THE DRIVERS PULL ON
EACH OTHER LIKE MAGNETS.
- I TELL YA, BOTH OF
THOSE GUYS HAVE GOTTA
BE GETTING TIRED BY NOW.
- OH, I'M SURE THEY ARE.
BUT THEY'RE PROBABLY
TOO FAR INTO IT TO NOTICE.
IF YOU START TO NOTICE THAT
YOU'RE GETTING TIRED
OR WORN DOWN, THAT'S REAL BAD.
IT'S THE FIRST SIGN THAT
YOUR CONCENTRATION
IS STARTING TO SLIP.
MY BET IS THAT WHEN THIS
BATTLE FINDS AN ENDING,
IT'S GONNA HAPPEN FROM
OUT OF NOWHERE.
- NO! I'M NOT LOSING THIS!
THIS BATTLE TONIGHT'S ALL ABOUT
MOTIVATION! AND I'VE GOT IT!
BASTARD, NEVER HAD
TO WORK FOR A DIME,
HE CAN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT I COME FROM.
YOU CAN'T BUY THE DETERMINATION
I'VE GOT! I CAN'T LOSE,
THIS IS NOT HOW
THIS MOVIE ENDS!
- Itsuki: THIS TURNED INTO
ONE HECK OF A BATTLE, HUH?
- YEAH, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THEY'VE BEEN DRIVING ALL NIGHT
IN THIS DOWNPOUR
AND THEY HAVEN'T TAKEN
A SINGLE BREAK.
- I'M IMPRESSED WATARU COULD BE
THAT EXTREME WITH HIS DRIVING.
HE'S REALLY GOING FOR
THE THROAT OF THAT FD.
THAT TAKES A WHOLE LOT OF GUTS.
OF COURSE I GOTTA ADMIRE ANYBODY
COOL ENOUGH TO DRIVE A LEVIN.
- YOU ACTUALLY
ADMIRE MY BROTHER?
- OH, HELL YEAH.
- WELL, DON'T BOTHER. WHAT'S SO
GREAT ABOUT HIM ANYWAY?
- QUESTION IS
WHAT'S NOT SO GREAT?
HE'S REALLY COOL,
HE'S INTO HIS CAR,
AND THE GUY DRIVES
LIKE A MANIAC.
IT'S SO BADASS HE'S DECIDED
TO STICK WITH HIS LEVIN
INSTEAD OF SWITCHING TO
SOMETHING HOT AND FLASHY.
- HE HASN'T SWITCHED BECAUSE
HE'S BROKE AS A PAY PHONE.
'COURSE, I DON'T HAVE
ANY MONEY EITHER.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
POINTING FINGERS.
- I'M SO JEALOUS OF THOSE TWO,
HITTING IT OFF LIKE NOTHIN'.
- THE LEVIN'S STARTING TO
SHIMMY AROUND COMPARED
TO HOW SHE WAS A FEW MILES BACK.
HE MUST BE STARTING TO BURN OUT.
I GUESS IT'S TIME TO START
MAKING SOME OF MY MOVES.
PUT THE PRESSURE ON, AND SEE
WHAT IT TAKES TO CRACK THIS GUY!
- I KNEW HE'D DO THIS. TRYING TO
PUSH ME INTO MAKING A MISTAKE.
BUT IT AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN. I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE WEARING OUT.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF
WHO GOES DOWN FIRST.
- Nobuhiko: YOU'RE HERE.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU TO BE HIDING
OUT IN SOME CORNER ALL NIGHT.
BUT IF I HAD TO GUESS I'D SAY
YOU'RE HERE TO ROOT FOR KEISUKE.
- Kyoko: YEAH. SORRY, NOBUHIKO.
- AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE'RE NOT AT WAR
WITH EACH OTHER.
A CAR RACE. IT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE FUN.
CHEER FOR WHOEVER YOU LIKE,
IT'S ALL THE SAME TO ME.
- ♪ GROWING ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE YOU HIGHER,
BABY, I WANT YOU ♪
♪ JUST ANOTHER REFLECTION
INTO YOUR EYES ♪
- SAD TO SEE A TINY BIT OF
RAIN MAKE YOUR CARS
GO ALL WOBBLY LIKE THAT.
FR'S SURE ARE PATHETIC
LITTLE CLUNKERS.
AND BESIDES, IF YOU
WANNA WIN THIS,
THERE ARE PLENTY OF
THINGS YOU CAN DO.
THERE'S NOT A REASON
IN THE WORLD
TO LET THIS RACE RUN ITS
NATURAL COURSE.
- ♪ I'LL TAKE YOU AWAY
FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ I WANNA BE THE NIGHT,
I REALLY WANT IT, BABE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANNA SHOW
YOU MY LOVE ♪
- DAMMIT. FEELS LIKE HE'S
TAILGATING ME.
I CAN'T SHAKE HIM.
WHAT'S GOING ON,
I'M FALLING OFF PACE?
I MUST BE MORE TIRED
THAN I THOUGHT.
I HAVE TO PUSH IT HARDER!
- ♪ ROLLING, ROLLING, ROLLING ♪
- ( tires screeching )
- ♪ BURNING, BURNING, BURNING ♪
- CRAP, THIS ISN'T GOOD!
I'M STARTING TO LOSE CONTROL.
I JUST HOPE MY CONCENTRATION
HASN'T GONE ON ME.
- Ryosuke: HUMAN CONCENTRATION
DOESN'T LAST THAT LONG.
ANYONE CAN ONLY FOCUS FULL
FOR ABOUT THIRTY MINUTES.
AFTER THAT, THINGS START
TO FALL APART.
- HOLD ON. DON'T THE PROS GO FOR
LIKE TWO, THREE HOURS AT A TIME?
FIVE HUNDRED MILES? HOW THE HECK
DO THEY PULL THAT OFF?
- WELL, THEY MIGHT BE
PART OF A BIG RACE.
BUT THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO GIVE A 100% THE ENTIRE TIME.
THAT'S WHY CIRCUITS USUALLY HAVE
THOSE LONG STRAIGHTAWAYS WHERE
YOU CAN EASE UP SOME.
- BUT ON THESE WINDING ROADS,
YOU DON'T GET THAT.
NO REAL PLACE FOR YOU
TO TAKE ANY KIND OF BREAK.
- Ryosuke: THE VISIBILITY IS
BAD BECAUSE OF THE RAIN.
THE ROAD IS SLICK.
YOU CAN'T RELAX.
- SO WHEN ONE OF
THEM FINALLY SLIPS UP,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS GONNA HAPPEN?
HOW BAD'LL IT BE?
WELL, FIRST YOUR DECISION
MAKING SLIPS,
THEN YOUR REFLEXES SLOW DOWN.
A MINOR STRESS
CAN TURN MAJOR, FAST.
YOUR ABILITY TO MULTITASK
WILL BEGIN TO FAIL.
THE END WILL SEEM TO
COME FROM NOWHERE.
- JUST DO YOUR BEST OUT THERE,
BABY. I'M ON YOUR SIDE,
AND I KNOW YOU CAN WIN THIS.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
- ♪ DON'T BE SO SHY ♪
♪ JUMPING YOU GOT THE POWER ♪
♪ SHAKING YOUR BODY GUIDES YOU
MOVING INTO THE FIRE ♪
♪ I WANNA TELL YOU ♪
♪ JUST ANOTHER REFLECTION
INTO YOUR EYES ♪
- NOW THE RAIN'S REALLY STARTING
TO COME DOWN.
- YEP, THIS'LL TOTALLY
WIPE 'EM OUT.
- ♪ ONCE MORE ♪
♪ I WANNA BE THE NIGHT
I REALLY WANT IT, BABE ♪
♪ I WANNA SHOW YOU MY LOVE ♪
♪ I WANNA BE YOUR NIGHT
OH, BABY, LET ME TRY ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE YOU AWAY
FOR A WHILE ♪
- Wataru: CAN'T SEE!
ALL RIGHT, UP NEXT SHOULD
BE A WIDE CORNER
I CAN TAKE AT MID-SPEED.
- ♪ BURNING, BURNING, BURNING ♪
♪ DANCING, DANCING, DANCING ♪
♪ SHOCK ME, SHOCK ME,
SHOCK ME ♪
- ( Wataru panting )
SON OF A BITCH!
- YOU OKAY, MAN?
- YEAH, I'M COOL. I MANAGED TO
STOP HER, LIKE, A CENTIMETER
AWAY FROM THE CONCRETE WALL.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
YOU MUST'VE SPUN OUT AT
A DECENT ANGLE, THEN.
- THAT'S JUST PART OF
MY DRIVING TECHNIQUE.
NOW, THIS MIGHT SOUND LIKE AN
EXCUSE BUT I GOTTA TELL YA.
I KNOW, OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD,
THE EXACT LOCATION OF ALL
THE GUTTERS ON THIS RUN.
I'M NOT KIDDING,
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF 'EM.
BUT STILL, IN THE
SPLIT SECOND I REACHED
TO CRANK MY WIPER BLADES,
ONE OF THOSE DAMN GUTTERS
GOT UNDER ME AND TRIPPED ME UP.
I CAN'T SAY IT'S ANYTHING ELSE
OTHER THAN BAD FREAKIN' LUCK.
I CAN BARELY BELIEVE IT MYSELF.
I GUESS THAT'S JUST ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
LOSE YOUR CONCENTRATION
FOR A MOMENT, LOSE THE RACE.
- I JUST GOT WORD THAT
WATARU SPUN OUT.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE LOST TONIGHT.
- ( dejected moans )
- SO, KEISUKE WON.
- YOU KNOW, I KNEW
GOING INTO THIS ,
THERE WAS NO WAY WE COULD LOSE.
THIS IS ANNOYING.
- DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL YA.
I CAN SAY THAT
I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN
YOU WOULD HAVE
TAKEN THE DOWNHILL
IF IT WEREN'T FOR THE
TORRENTIAL RAIN.
- HE DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
- NO, HE DOES NOT.
- I LOST THE BATTLE.
- WE LOST. WE LOST EVERYTHING.
RYOSUKE, YOU AND YOUR CREW,
YOU'RE OPERATING
ON A WHOLE DIFFERENT LEVEL.
- Fumihiro: ALRIGHT, FELLAS,
WE'RE OUTTA HERE! PICK UP ALL
YOUR CRAP, OKAY?
DON'T LEAVE ANYTHING BEHIND!
- ( signing in Japanese )
♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪