- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- KEISUKE...
IN ORDER TO WIN, YOU'LL HAVE
TO APPROACH THIS BATTLE
FROM A DIFFERENT ANGLE.
YOU NEED TO TRUST ME. THIS ISN'T
EXACTLY THE KIND OF THING
I WOULD NORMALLY ASK YOU TO DO.
- I'M OPEN TO IDEAS, BRO.
- YOU'RE TAKING THE LEAD?
- THAT'S THE PLAN.
UNLIKE MY FRIEND HERE,
I DON'T NEED TO STUDY
MY OPPONENT'S EVERY MOVE
TO KNOW HOW TO WIN.
BESIDES, I CAN'T AFFORD
TO DRAG THIS OUT.
MY CAR IS A LITTLE HEAVY.
IF I LET UP, THEY COULD USE
THAT TO THEIR ADVANTAGE.
I'LL MAKE IT QUICK.
- ( he chuckles )
- DON'T BE TOO SURE.
I DON'T NEED TO REMIND YOU,
YOU DO HAVE A TENDENCY
TO GET A LITTLE COMPLACENT WHEN
YOU THINK THERE'S NO CHANCE
YOU COULD LOSE.
I'M NOT SAYING I
THINK YOU WILL.
BUT THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A SURE THING.
- WORRYING LIKE THAT WILL
GIVE YOU AN ULCER YOU KNOW.
IT'S LIKE I SAID, I'LL KEEP
UP THE MOMENTUM
AND THIS WILL BE
OVER PRETTY QUICK.
THEY'RE NEVER GONNA EVEN
KNOW WHAT HIT'EM.
- I DON'T KNOW 'BOUT THIS.
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO PULL IT OFF,
BUT IT SURE AS HELL
WON'T BE EASY.
- NOBODY SAID THIS
WOULDN'T BE CHALLENGING.
- ASSUMING EVERYTHING GOES
ACCORDING TO YOUR SIMULATION,
- WHAT'S THE ABSOLUTE
MOST TIME I CAN GIVE HIM
AT THE TURNING POINT?
- I'D SAY...
SEVEN SECONDS.
- WHAT?!
- SEVEN SECONDS?
- OUR PERFECT RECORD
IS RIDING ON THIS, KEISUKE...
JUST BE SURE TO
KEEP THAT IN MIND.
- RIGHT.
- OKAY, DRIVERS TO
THE STARTING LINE!
- ALRIGHT EVERYONE,
ON MY COUNT!
FOUR... THREE... TWO...
ONE... GO!
- ( up-tempo music playing )
- AWAY THEY GO.
HOSHINO KNOWS WHAT HE NEEDS
TO DO IN ORDER TO WIN.
WHEN YOU'VE DRIVEN AS LONG AS HE
HAS, YOU LEARN A FEW THINGS.
- DON'T LET UP.
NOT EVEN FOR A SECOND.
C'MON BIG GUY. GIVE IT
EVERYTHING YOU GOT
AND THEN SOME.
- LOOKS LIKE IT'S STARTED.
- YEP, LOOKS LIKE IT.
- KEISUKE'S UP AGAINST
KOUZOU HOSHINO.
MOST PEOPLE KNOW
HIM AS GOD FOOT
BECAUSE OF HIS EXPERTISE
WITH ACCELERATORS.
EVEN SOMEONE LIKE KEISUKE
HAS GOT TO BE FEELING
A LITTLE NERVOUS.
- JUST MEETING WITH THEM LAST
NIGHT MADE ME NERVOUS.
I CAN'T PUT MY FINGER ON IT, BUT
SOMETHING IS SERIOUSLY OFF
ABOUT THOSE GUYS.
- TRY NOT TO GET PSYCHED OUT.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE GOING UP
AGAINST GOD ARM.
AND WE'LL NEED STAY ON TOP OF
OUR GAME FOR THAT, ALRIGHT?
-HERE.
WE.
GO!
DORYAA!
- WELL, WELL... YOU'VE GOT
A FEW TRICKS UP YOUR SLEEVE,
PRETTY SMOOTH
FOR SUCH A HEAVY RIDE.
- AGE COMES BEFORE BEAUTY,
LITTLE MAN! EAT MY DUST!
( tires screeching )
- LOOKS LIKE THE RACE
HAS ALREADY STARTED.
- WAIT A SECOND, WHY ARE THEY
STARTING WITH THE HILL CLIMB?
- IT'S NOT JUST GONNA BE
JUST AN UPHILL.
I HEARD SOMEBODY
SAY THEY'RE RACING
AN UPHILL AND DOWNHILL TONIGHT.
- THEY'RE DOING
A COMBINATION RACE?
- THAT'S RIGHT. A HILL
CLIMB FOLLOWED BY
A DOWNHILL IS ONE RUN.
THEY KEEP RUNNING THE
COURSE OVER AND OVER
UNTIL THERE IS A CLEAR WINNER.
- I HAVEN'T SEEN KOUZOU
HOSHINO RACE IN FOREVER,
NOT SINCE HE WAS STILL DRIVING
THAT R32 AROUND.
MAN THAT OLD GUY CAN
REALLY DRIVE.
I WENT TO THIS RANDOM MEET AT
TSUKUBA CIRCUIT JUST CAUSE
SOMEBODY TOLD ME HOSHINO WAS
GONNA BE RACING THAT DAY.
I GOT TO SEE HIM ACTUALLY DRIFT
HIS R32 THE ENTIRE WAY
THROUGH THE FINAL CORNER.
SEEING SOMETHING LIKE
THAT ISN'T THE KIND OF THING
YOU CAN EVER FORGET.
THE ATTESA-ETS ON THE
GT-R CAN BE A REAL BITCH
IF YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
AND YOU CAN FORGET TRYING
TO DRIFT WITH IT,
IT'S TOO HEAVY.
IT JUST WASN'T DESIGNED
FOR THAT KIND OF DRIVING.
THE SECOND THE ETS
DETECTS A TAIL SLIDING,
IT KICKS IN AND STARTS TO SPIN
THE FRONT TIRES.
- I DIDN'T KNOW THAT!
BUT TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
I'M CLUELESS ABOUT FOUR
WHEEL DRIVES.
- IT'S LIKE THIS, IF YOU PULLED
BACK YOUR COUNTER STEER
AND STEPPED ON THE ACCELERATOR,
YOU COULDN'T MAINTAIN
A SLIDE ANGLE.
WHICH IS WHY I PREFER THE FR
OVER THE GT-R.
THE TRACTION FROM THE FRONT
TIRES WILL AUTOMATICALLY TAKE
HOLD OF THE ROAD AND THE CAR
WILL STOP DRIFTING INSTANTLY.
IT'S A LIABILITY IF YOU ASK ME.
AND AS IF THAT'S NOT BAD ENOUGH,
THE ATTESA-ETS DECIDES HOW
TO DISTRIBUTE POWER
TO THE FRONT TIRES AS YOU
STEP ON THE ACCELERATOR.
WHICH MEANS THAT IF YOU RELY
ON YOUR LIGHT FOOTWORK
ON THE THROTTLE, YOU'RE ONLY
MAKING IT ALL THE MORE DIFFICULT
TO MAINTAIN A SOLID DRIFT.
- BUT I THOUGHT YOU SAID
HOSHINO'S GT-R DRIFTED
IN THE BATTLE YOU SAW HIM RUN?
- YEAH THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT
SO MEMORABLE...
CHIEF WAS THERE TOO AND EVEN HE
COULDN'T EXPLAIN HOW HE DID IT.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THE WHOLE EXPERIENCE NEARLY LEFT
HIM COMPLETELY SPEECHLESS.
- WISH I BEEN THERE TO SEE THAT.
- I'M NOT GONNA LIE,
IT WAS PRETTY HILARIOUS.
ANYWAYS, LIKE I WAS
SAYING, I THINK HOSHINO MIGHT BE
THE ONLY GUY WHO COULD PULL
SOMETHING LIKE THAT OFF.
- I'M STARTING TO GET WHY THE
CHIEF WAS PUSHING SO HARD FOR US
TO COME AND WATCH THIS
PARTICULAR RACE.
- ME TOO. I GUARANTEE YOU, THERE
ISN'T A SINGLE PERSON OUT HERE
THAT COULD WORK A PEDAL
THE WAY KOUZOU HOSHINO CAN.
I MEAN THEY DON'T CALL
THE GUY GOD FOOT
BECAUSE HE CAN WALK
ON WATER, YOU KNOW.
- THE CHIEF WAS SPOUTING OFF
ABOUT TONIGHT'S RACE EARLIER ON.
HE SAID HE'D BE SHOCKED IF
PROJECT D WAS ABLE TO WIN,
AND I THINK I SEE
WHAT HE MEANT BY THAT.
- YEAH. I DO KNOW ONE THING
FOR SURE THOUGH...
THIS RACE IS GOING TO BE
SOMETHING ELSE.
- I'VE HAD THE GT-R THREE-TWO,
THE THREE-THREE, AND
THE THREE-FOUR.
NOTHING ELSE ON THE ROAD
HANDLES LIKE THESE BABIES.
AFTER I GOT BEHIND THE WHEEL
OF MY FIRST THREE-TWO,
I KNEW I'D FINALLY FOUND THE
RIDE FOR ME.
AND I GOT THE LARGER SECOND
GENERATION THREE-THREE,
WHICH TURNED OUT TO BE A
TOTAL DISAPPOINTMENT.
THAT CAR WAS A WASTE OF TIME.
READY, SET.
DORYAA!
IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG FOR
ME TO GET RID OF THAT
PIECE OF CRAP 3-3 AND
BUY ANOTHER 3-2.
THIS IS THE FOURTH GT-R
I'VE OWNED.
THE GT-R THREE-FOUR!
OKAY...
HE'S KEEPING UP.
NO BIG SURPRISE THERE.
- DAMN, HE'S FAST.
I LET MYSELF GET COCKY BECAUSE
OF ALL THE MODIFICATIONS WE DID
TO THE FD.
THAT WAS A BIG MISTAKE.
MAN, THIS GT-R DRIVES
LIKE IT'S ON RAILS!
- SITTING IN WITH
HOSHINO DURING A RACE
IS PRETTY FREAKIN' WILD DUDE.
- I BET IT IS. IS IT TRUE THAT
HE TALKS TO HIMSELF?
- HE YELLS "DORYAA"
OR "BRING IT ON".
BUT I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY KNOWS WHY.
- MAN THAT IS SO WEIRD.
THEN AGAIN, I GUESS EVERY
DRIVER HAS HIS LITTLE QUIRKS.
MAYBE THAT'S JUST THE WAY
HE KEEPS HIS FOCUS.
BUT WHATEVER, IT WORKS.
- SEEMS TO ME THAT IF I TRIED
THAT IT'D HURT MY CONCENTRATION
MORE THAN HELP.
BUT I DO KNOW THAT EITHER
WAY I WOULD FEEL LIKE
ONE CRAZY BASTARD,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- YEAH. MOST PEOPLE CLAM UP
WHEN THEY ARE TRYING
TO CONCENTRATE, BUT HOSHINO
ISN'T MOST PEOPLE.
- LISTEN TO THEM. IT'S
ADORABLE HOW HARD
THEY'RE TRYING TO
FIGURE IT ALL OUT.
CONCENTRATION THROUGH SHOUTING?
AW, HOW I MISS BEING
YOUNG AND NAIVE.
- BRING IT ON!
LET'S DO THIS!
- DESPITE WHAT SOME MAY THINK...
HOSHINO HAS A TENDENCY TO
OVERTHINK HIS STRATEGY.
THE MORE HE THINKS
ABOUT SOMETHING,
THE MORE WORKED UP HE GETS.
TALKING TO HIMSELF KEEPS HIM
FROM CONCENTRATING TOO HARD.
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE CAME UP
WITH IT.
BUT IT REALLY SEEMS TO HELP
HIM BEHIND THE WHEEL.
MY CURIOSITY SOMETIMES GETS THE
BETTER OF ME...
I HAVE TO WONDER WHAT HOSHINO
WOULD BE LIKE AS A DRIVER
WITHOUT HIS LITTLE TECHNIQUE.
I KNOW ONE THING FOR
SURE THOUGH...
AS WILD AS HE IS NOW,
I DOUBT HE'D BE THE KIND OF
DRIVER I WANT ON MY TEAM.
- DON'T MESS WITH ME!
- TRY AND KEEP A LEVEL HEAD
OUT THERE, OLD FRIEND.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
DON'T GO WASTING TIME
SHOWING OFF...
YOU'RE NOT A KID ANYMORE.
- WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE FOR
A COLD FRONT RIGHT NOW.
- LET ME GET YOU A DRINK, SIR.
YOU GOTTA STAY HYDRATED.
HERE YOU GO.
- APPRECIATE IT.
- YOU ARE SWEATING A LOT.
YOU SURE IT'S JUST THE
WEATHER, SIR?
ONCE YOU GET TO BE MY AGE, HEAT
CAN REALLY DO A NUMBER ON YOU.
- MAN-O-MAN... I FREAKIN'
LOVE THIS CAR!
THE THREE-TWO I HAD BEFORE THIS,
HAD ITS SHARE OF MINOR PROBLEMS
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT CAME TO THE
UNDER STEERING.
NOT THE THREE-FOUR THOUGH...
THIS CAR WAS MADE FOR ME.
PEOPLE THAT DON'T KNOW ANY
BETTER THINK MERCEDES
AND FERRARIS ARE THE BEST
CARS ON THE STREET
JUST 'CAUSE THEY COST
AN ARM AND A LEG.
I COULD BUY BOTH CARS TOMORROW
AND NEITHER ONE OF THEM
WOULD HOLD A CANDLE TO THE GT-R.
THEY'RE THE WAY TO GO.
GT-R, BABY!
OH YEAH!
COME ON!
- TELL ME SOMETHING.
IN OTHER BATTLES, IT SEEMS
LIKE YOU PRETTY MUCH
LET KEISUKE DO WHATEVER
THE HELL HE WANTS.
I WAS JUST
WONDERING WHAT IT WAS
THAT MAKES TONIGHT SO DIFFERENT.
- IN CASE YOU HADN'T NOTICED,
THESE GENTLEMAN AREN'T YOUR RUN
OF THE MILL STREET RACERS.
- TRUST ME,
I DEFINITELY NOTICED.
- THEY'RE AT AN ADVANTAGE.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE UPHILL,
TIRE MANAGEMENT IS BY
FAR THE IMPORTANT FACTOR.
WE HAVE TO PLAY THIS SMART.
WE TRY TO COMPETE WITH THE FOUR
WHEEL DRIVE GT-R,
THE TIRES ON KEISUKE'S FD ARE
BOUND TO WEAR OUT.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT KEISUKE'S
ACCELERATOR WORK?
I MEAN, YOU HAVE TO ADMIT THAT
HE'S GOTTEN A LOT BETTER LATELY.
- I KNOW HE HAS.
THAT'S WHY HE ISN'T MY MAIN
CONCERN AT THE MOMENT.
SOMEONE ELSE IS WELL VERSED
IN ACCELERATORS.
- YEAH. AND I'M GUESSING HE
GOES BY THE NICKNAME GOD FOOT.
- HOLDING OFF ON THE HILL CLIMB
AND MAKING A MOVE
ON THE DOWNHILL
IS PRETTY MUCH OUR ONLY
OPTION NOW.
- I DO SEE WHAT YOU'RE SAYING...
BUT IT JUST SEEMS TO ME...
THAT SEVEN SECONDS IS CUTTING
IT A LITTLE BIT CLOSE.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT
THIS RYOSUKE?
WHAT IF SOMETHING GOES
WRONG OUT THERE?
THOSE SEVEN SECONDS WILL STILL
GIVE US THE WINDOW WE NEED.
A RACE CAN CHANGE DRAMATICALLY
IN LESS TIME.
I'M ASKING A LOT OF KEISUKE,
BUT HE'S FULLY CAPABLE OF
PULLING THIS OFF.
I'M CERTAIN OF IT.
YOU WERE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT WHEN
YOU SAID HIS ACCELERATOR WORK
HAD IMPROVED, FUMIHIRO.
BUT WHETHER HE'S SMART ENOUGH
TO PUT IT TO GOOD USE...
THAT REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
- I DON'T KNOW, BRO. THIS IS
ONE HELL OF A RISKY MOVE.
I HOPE I CAN MAKE IT WORK...
BUT I DON'T KNOW, THIS GEEZER
IS PRETTY DAMN FAST.
IF I CAN'T REGAIN THE SEVEN
SECOND LEAD ON THE DOWNHILL,
ALL OF THIS WILL
HAVE BEEN FOR NOTHING.
REGAINING A LEAD IS A TALL ORDER
IN JUST ABOUT ANY RACE,
AND THROWING STRATEGY INTO THE
MIX DOESN'T HELP.
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T
BE SURPRISED...
BRO WOULDN'T ASK ME TO DO
SOMETHING IF IT WAS EASY.
DON'T GET COMFY, GRAMPS.
I'M ABOUT TO TAKE THE LEAD.
- KEEP IT STEADY...
NOT JUST YET.
- I GOT THIS. IF BRO THINKS
I CAN DO IT, I KNOW I CAN.
CONCENTRATE...
JUST FOCUS ON MOVING
YOUR RIGHT FOOT!
- YEA BABY!
- BADASS!
- I'M TELLIN YA... HOSHINO'S
GOT THIS THING IN THE BAG!
- NO WAY THAT FD CAN TAKE
THE LEAD AWAY FROM HIM NOW.
- WHAT'S UP WITH PROJECT D?
I HEARD THEY HAD AN AMAZING
DRIVER RACING TONIGHT.
- YOU DUMBASS! HOSHINO EATS
CHUMPS LIKE THAT FOR BREAKFAST.
THEIR FD COULD NEVER KEEP UP
WITH HIS GT-R-THREE-FOUR.
- THEY SHOULD GO AHEAD
AND CALL THIS THING,
SAVE US ALL SOME TIME.
PURPLE SHADOW IS
GONNA DESTROY PROJECT D.
- I SEE WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO
DO. THAT'S AN IMPRESSIVE MOVE.
PRETTY GOOD FOR A KID HIS AGE.
THERE AREN'T MANY DRIVERS
NOWADAYS THAT WOULD EVEN ATTEMPT
WHAT HE'S TRYING TO PULL OFF.
IF I WERE IN HIS POSITION,
I'D MADE A MOVE FOR
THE LEAD ALREADY.
BUT I'M NOT KNOWN
FOR MY PATIENCE.
THAT STILL DOESN'T MEAN I
SHOULD UNDERESTIMATE
WHAT THIS KID COULD
BE CAPABLE OF.
NOW LET'S GO!
- PROJECT D
KEEPS FALLING BEHIND.
MAN, WHAT'S THE FD'S DEAL?
THIS RACE COULD BE OVER
PRETTY SOON.
ANOTHER FLAWLESS VICTORY
FOR THE PURPLE SHADOW, HUH?
- NOT QUITE YET.
LOOKS LIKE PROJECT D IS WORKING
THIS FROM A DIFFERENT ANGLE
BY USING THE VARIABLE
SPEED RULE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THE GT-R HAS THE ADVANTAGE
ON THE HILL CLIMB
BECAUSE OF ITS
SUPERIOR TRACTION.
BUT THE FD ACTUALLY HAS THE
ADVANTAGE ON THE DOWNHILL
BECAUSE IT'S LIGHTER.
IF KEISUKE DOESN'T PUT TOO
MUCH STRESS ON HIS TIRES
DURING THE HILL CLIMB,
THE DUDE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO MAKE A PLAY
FOR THE LEAD ON THE DOWNHILL.
- INTERESTING.
BUT WAIT, IF WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS TRUE
THEN THAT MEANS PROJECT D
IS TRYING TO OUTSMART
HOSHINO BY STAYING BEHIND?
- THEY'RE TAKING A HUGE
GAMBLE BY USING THIS STRATEGY.
NOT TO MENTION IT'S PRETTY
DAMN BALLSY OF THEM
TO TRY SOMETHING LIKE THIS ON
SOMEBODY LIKE KOUZOU HOSHINO.
IF THEY AREN'T ABLE TO CATCH UP
TO HIM IN TIME ON THE DOWNHILL,
THEY'LL GONNA BE TOTALLY SCREWED
- FOR REAL.
- THINGS ARE ABOUT TO GET
A LITTLE CRAZY.
THAT'S A BOLD MOVE,
RYOSUKE TAKAHASHI.
MAN, CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HOW
THIS'LL TURN OUT.
SERIOUSLY, KOUZOU HOSHINO IN AN
ALL-OUT DOWNHILL BATTLE
WITH KEISUKE TAKAHASHI.
THEY'RE BOTH AMAZING DRIVERS
WITH THE SOMETHING TO PROVE.
THE TWO OF THEM HAVE TO KNOW
WHAT'S AT STAKE HERE.
I GOT TO ADMIT DUDE, I'M GETTING
PUMPED JUST THINKING ABOUT IT.
- OKAY, I'M READY. THIS IS WHAT
ALL THAT TRAINING WAS FOR...
ALRIGHT. BRING IT ON OLD MAN!
TIME TO STOP LAGGING BEHIND.
THAT LEAD IS MINE.
- THEY'RE ALMOST HERE.
- I JUST HEARD PEOPLE SAYING
THAT KEISUKE'S RUNNING BEHIND...
THERE'S NO WAY THAT COULD
REALLY BE TRUE, RIGHT.
- WELL IT MIGHT BE.
YOU GOT TO ADMIT,
THE GT-R DOES HAVE HIM
AT A DISADVANTAGE.
- KEISUKE MUST FEEL LIKE CRAP
RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW I WOULD.
I THINK IT'S PROBABLY SAFE TO
SAY THAT HE'S NEVER HAD
THAT HAPPEN TO HIM BEFORE.
LOSING AN OPPONENT IN THE
MIDDLE OF A RACE LIKE THIS
COULD MAKE OR BREAK
YOU AS A DRIVER.
TRUST ME.
MAN, I'D HATE TO BE IN
HIS SHOES.
TRYING TO MAINTAIN
CONCENTRATION DURING A RACE
IS HARD ENOUGH WITHOUT HAVING
TO WORRY ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
YOU'RE GOING TO CATCH UP TO
THE OTHER DRIVER IN TIME.
AND WITH EVERYTHING ELSE
TO FOCUS ON.
- NO KIDDING.
- OH, PLEASE.
KEISUKE HAS WHAT IT TAKES.
- STAY FOCUSED.
KEEP UP THE PACE...
IF I'M GOING TO KEEP MY LINE
THROUGH THIS NEXT CORNER
I HAVE TO MAINTAIN THIS SPEED.
REMEMBER NOT TO PUT TOO MUCH
STRESS ON THE TIRES.
- ( tires screeching )
- AT THE END OF THE CORNER, OPEN
UP THE THROTTLE AND BOOK IT.
- I'M SURE YOU RECALL KEISUKE
ACTUALLY STARTED TO PERFECT
HIS ACCELERATOR WORK DURING
OUR BATTLES IN SAITAMA.
HE DIDN'T REALIZE HE NEEDED TO
UNTIL THEN.
IT COULDN'T HAVE
BEEN EASY FOR HIM
TO ACKNOWLEDGE
HIS SHORTCOMINGS,
BUT LOOK HOW MUCH HE'S IMPROVED
BECAUSE OF ALL THE HARD
WORK HE'S PUT IN.
EVEN I WAS SHOCKED BY
HOW QUICKLY
HE LEARNED THOSE TECHNIQUES.
AND BY HOW QUICKLY HE
MASTERED THEM.
- WHEN KEISUKE SETS HIS
MIND ON SOMETHING,
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME TILL
HE MAKES IT HAPPEN.
THIS BATTLE IS FAR FROM OVER.
IF HE WANTS TO WIN THIS THING,
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO PULL OUT
ALL THE STOPS.
- ( engines in the background )
- THEY'RE COMING!
- HEY WHO'S IN THE LEAD?
- DUDE, I THINK THAT'S
HOSHINO'S GT-R!
- THE FD IS NOWHERE
TO BE SEEN...
THIS ISN'T A BATTLE,
IT'S A DAMN MASSACRE!
- HERE WE GO!
WHOO-YA!
- ( laughing and cheering )
- HELL YEAH!
- HE'S SO COOL!
- TANGO WITH
MY THREE-FOUR
AND YOU'RE ONLY
GOING TO REGRET IT.
- YEAH! YOU CAN DO IT!
- ( cellphone rings )
- HELLO? HEY, KENTA.
HOW MANY SECONDS WAS IT?
OK, I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
THANKS FOR THE CALL.
HE SAID HE COUNTED AT THE
TURNAROUND. IT WAS SIX SECONDS.
JUST UNDER.
- I SEE...
NICELY DONE LITTLE BRO...
YOU WERE ABLE TO HOLD YOUR OWN
AGAINST SOMEONE YOU
COULDN'T EVEN SEE.
BUT DON'T EASE UP.
THE REAL GAMBLE IS
JUST BEGINNING.
- ( theme plays )