- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( engine revving )
- Takumi: MAN, I'M STILL
PUMPED FROM LAST NIGHT'S RACE.
THE WHOLE THING WAS LIKE
SOME KIND OF CRAZY DREAM.
- ( engine revving)
- ( tires screeching )
IT WAS MAINLY LUCK
THAT I WON, THOUGH.
IF RYOSUKE HAD BEEN
THE ONE TO TAKE THAT GUY ON,
PROJECT D WOULD'VE
HAD A SURE THING.
WHY DO THEY BOTHER
KEEPING A NOOB LIKE ME AROUND
WHEN I'M SUCH AN
OBVIOUS LIABILITY?
WILD CARD, NOTHING.
I'VE GOTTA GET BETTER.
AM I BEING CHASED?
HE'S FAST!
HE'S GAINING ON ME.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
SHOULD I LET YOU PASS,
OR SHOULD I JUST DUST
YOUR DUMB ASS AND TEACH
YOU SOME MANNERS?
WELL, AFRAID I DON'T FEEL
LIKE LETTING YOU PASS.
NOT AFTER LAST NIGHT. AND IT
SURE AS HELL IS NOT GONNA HAPPEN
ON MY HOME TURF.
- ( engine revs)
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
DOES THIS GUY HAVE IT
IN FOR ME OR WHAT?
WHO ARE YOU?
- ( birds chirping )
- ( water dripping )
- ( tires screeching )
- DAMN IT!
MR. ENIGMA HERE MIGHT
BE THE TOUGHEST OPPONENT
I'VE EVER SEEN ON AKINA.
THIS IS INSANE!
- ( tires screeching )
- ALL RIGHT,
YOU TRICKY BASTARD.
TIME TO SHOW YOU A FEW
THINGS I'VE GOT UP MY SLEEVE.
- ( tires screeching )
- HOLY SHIT!
IT'S OVER. I CAN'T BEAT
A DRIVER I CAN'T OUT-BRAKE.
SON OF A BITCH GOT ME.
DAD?
HEY, DAD, YOU AROUND?
OH, C'MON. WHERE THE HELL DID
YOU RUN OFF TO SO EARLY?
- HEY! SUP, MAN?
- HEY, HEY!
- WHAT'S UP, GUYS.
HEY, WHERE'S ITSUKI?
- OH, WELL, HE GOT OFF
WORK A LITTLE EARLY
TO PICK UP HIS EIGHT-FIVE
FROM THE SHOP.
- WE'RE GONNA GIVE THAT NEW
TURBO ENGINE HE HAD INSTALLED
A LITTLE TEST DRIVE
ON THE HILL TONIGHT.
- HA! SAY WHAT YOU WILL,
THAT EIGHT-FIVE WILL NEVER
BE A MATCH FOR ME AND MINE.
TURBO SCHMURBO, YOU CAN'T
GET BLOOD OUTTA THAT ROCK.
- WHATEVER. SO, BIG TIME,
SEEMS YOU HANDED A CERTIFIED
PRO HIS ASS LAST NIGHT, HUH?
I MEAN, HOLY CRAP!
IS THERE NOTHING YOU CAN'T DO?
- WELL...
- DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU, BUT I'M
PROUD TO SEE ONE OF OUR OWN
ON HIS WAY TO BECOMING A LEGEND.
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT SOMEBODY FROM
HERE WOULD EVER MANAGE THAT?
- WHATEVER KIND OF FIRE
THOSE PROJECT D BOYS
HAVE BEEN LIGHTING UNDER HIM,
IT SURE HAS DONE THE TRICK.
- I ALMOST FORGOT
I BEAT A CIRCUIT RACER.
IT FEELS LIKE A DREAM
I'VE WOKEN UP FROM.
I'VE HAD MY ASS HANDED
TO ME SINCE THEN
AND ON MY HOME TURF
OF ALL PLACES.
IT'S STUPID TO LET IT GET TO
ME LIKE THIS, BUT I DON'T KNOW,
HAS PROJECT D REALLY IMPROVED
MY DRIVING ALL THAT MUCH?
- ( car honking )
- ALL RIGHT, HEADS UP, GUYS.
- DA-DA-DA-DUM.
BEHOLD EIGHT KINDS OF KICK ASS.
( laughs)
LOOK UPON ME
AND DESPAIR, MORTALS.
THIS BABY IS GONNA RENDER
YOUR SKILLS OBSOLETE.
- ( tires screeching )
- I THINK YOU'RE GONNA
EAT YOUR WORDS, MY FRIEND.
THE TURBO'S PUTTING
YOU THROUGH THE PACES.
- SURE. WHATEVER YOU SAY.
LIKE I'VE GOT ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- ( engine revving )
- ( Itsuki gasps )
HOLY CRAP, TAKUMI.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
DUDE, I JUST PULLED OFF
A POWER SLIDE.
MY WILDEST DREAMS
HAVE BECOME A REALITY.
- SETTLE DOWN MAN.
DON'T START PATTING YOURSELF
ON THE BACK YET.
HEY, WE'RE BEING CHASED.
- ( engine revving )
- IS THIS MANIAC GONNA TRY TO
PASS US ON THE STRAIGHTAWAY?
- ( engine revving )
- HE'S FAST. WHAT
KINDA CAR IS THAT?
- IS THAT THE SAME GUY
FROM THIS MORNING?
- AN S-ONE-FIVE SILVIA.
- NO, DIFFERENT CAR.
- TWO HUNDRED AND FIFTY
HORSEPOWER IS JUST DEMONIC.
WAY TOO FAST FOR A COUPLE OF
CLUNKERS LIKE OURS TO KEEP UP.
- SO IS IT JUST ME OR DO
YOU GET THE FEELING
WE'RE A COUPLE OF BOX TURTLES
THAT'RE BEING LAPPED
BY A JACKRABBIT, HUH?
- Iketani: WHO YOU CALLING A
BOX TURTLE, JACKASS? HUH? HUH?
- Kenji: OW! WHAT THE HELL'S
WRONG WITH YOU?
STOP HITTING ME. OUCH! C'MON!
- Itsuki: EVEN AT PEAK
PERFORMANCE, THE THREE-AU ENGINE
USUALLY ONLY GROSSES
ABOUT EIGHTY HORSEPOWER.
SO, ANY WAY YOU SLICE IT,
ONE HUNDRED AND FIFTY IS ALMOST
DOUBLE WHAT SHE USED TO HAVE.
AND IMAGINE THE REAR
ACTUALLY SLIDES WHEN
WHEN I OPEN UP THIS BABY'S
ACCELERATOR ON THE HILL CLIMB.
IT'S ALMOST TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
GOD, I'M SO IN LOVE
WITH THIS CAR,
I COULD ELOPE WITH IT
AND HAVE CHILDREN!
- WE KNOW HOW IT IS, DUDE.
THERE'S NOTHING IN THE WORLD
MAKES A MAN FEEL LIKE A MAN
QUITE LIKE A FRESHLY
RE-TOOLED RIDE.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK, TAKUMI?
WAS HAVING THIS THING
OUTFITTED WITH A TURBO
WORTH ALL THE TROUBLE?
- I DUNNO.
IT FELT A LITTLE WEIRD TO ME.
I MEAN THE CAR DEFINITELY HAS
MORE POWER NOW, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- BUT, ALL IN ALL, IT'S
STRENGTHS ARE JUST DIFFERENT
THAN MY OWN RIDE, SO IT'D
TAKE SOME GETTING USED TO.
- IT'S BECAUSE OF
THE TORQUE, I BET.
WITH A TURBO ENGINE YOU GET
A HELL OF A LOT MORE PUNCH
FROM YOUR ACCELERATION
THAN A TYPICAL NA.
- THAT'S TRUE.
WHEN YOU'VE GOT THAT MUCH POWER
THE STEERING BECOMES A
REAL ENDURANCE TEST.
BUT YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
CHECK OUT YOUR DAMPER.
I THINK IT MIGHT
BE A LITTLE OFF.
- ( all exclaim )
- IF YOU REALLY WANNA
MAKES THIS BABY FASTER,
IT'S MORE A QUESTION OF HOW
IT HANDLES THAN ANYTHING.
YOU'VE GOTTA GET THAT
ACCELERATOR TO OPEN UP
WHILE YOU'RE CORNERING.
I MEAN, THE LIMITS ARE LOW.
SO, THERE'S A POSSIBILITY IT
MIGHT DRIFT ANYWAY, BUT...
- ( all gasp )
- UH, GUYS, WHY THE HELL ARE
YOU ALL STARING AT ME LIKE THAT?
- OKAY, AM I GOING CRAZY?
- I DON'T THINK SO, BUDDY,
I HEARD HIM TOO.
- Y'KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT
ON THE MONEY THERE, DUDE.
ITSUKI'S EIGHT-FIVE
IS A COMMUTER VEHICLE.
IT'S DAMPERS AND SPRING SYSTEM
AREN'T DESIGNED AROUND A TURBO.
HEY, DON'T TAKE THIS THE
WRONG WAY, BIG TIME,
BUT I NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS
THOUGHT I'D HEAR WORDS LIKE
THAT COMIN' OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
- AMAZING, YOU'VE GONE FROM
MORON TO SAVANT OVERNIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT, I WENT THERE.
- SAVANT. THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
WAY OF PUTTING IT, ACTUALLY.
WHAT THE HELL THEY'D
DO TO YOU IN PROJECT D?
- NOT A THING, SERIOUSLY.
IF THOSE GUYS HEARD ME TALKIN'
LIKE THIS THEY'D BE CRACKING UP.
- ( tires screeching )
- THAT'S THE CAR FROM EARLIER.
- WELL, HEY THERE,
FELLOW RACING ENTHUSIASTS.
SORRY ABOUT ALL THAT
BACK THERE,
BUT WHEN I SEE A
COUPLE OF STREETERS
I JUST CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
BY THE LOOKS OF YOU, YOU TWO
HAVE GOT TO BE FROM AROUND HERE.
ME AND MY BUDDY HERE
ARE FROM TOKYO.
SO FAR OUR TRIP HAS TURNED OUT
TO BE A DISAPPOINTMENT.
- YOU'D THINK WITH
ROADS LIKE THESE
THE PLACE'D BE
SWARMING WITH TALENT.
- HUH? HEY.
NOW, THERE'S A
RARE SIGHT FOR YA.
THIS IS A GENUINE
SOHC ENGINE.
YOU ACTUALLY GOT AN EIGHT FIVE
FITTED WITH A TURBO? SERIOUSLY?
- WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT,
THERE'S ENOUGH ROOM LEFT
OVER IN THE ENGINE CHASSIS
TO HOUSE A FAMILY OF FOUR.
- NOW DON'T BE MEAN.
THEY DO HAVE A FRONT MOUNT
INTERCOOLER, AFTER ALL.
THAT'LL EXPLODE IF
YOU SO MUCH AS TAP IT.
- ( chuckles )
YOU COULDN'T PAY ME TO DRIVE
THIS THING. I'D BE TOO SCARED!
- SO, ANY CHANCE YOU'VE EVER
SEEN A CIRCUIT RACE FIRSTHAND?
- SORRY. NOT ANY AROUND HERE.
- HMM.
WELL, IF YOU EVER WANNA RISE
ABOVE BEING A STREETER,
YOU SHOULD SEE ONE.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN A PART OF
ALMOST EVERY MAJOR CIRCUIT EVENT
IN RECENT MEMORY. EVEN THE
ONES ALONG THE PENINSULA.
THE MOUNTAIN PASSES
IN A SINKHOLE
LIKE THIS ARE NO COMPARISON.
OF COURSE, THAT MIGHT BE
JUST AS WELL FOR YOU GUYS.
I DON'T THINK YOUR
LITTLE EIGHT FIVE
WOULD BE WORTH A CRAP IN
A CIRCUIT RACE.
- HEY, SHUT UP!
- ASSHOLE. WHO THE HELL
YOU THINK YOU ARE,
TALKING ABOUT OUR RIDE LIKE
IT'S ANY OF YOUR DAMN BUSINESS?
IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU'RE FULL O' CRAP.
OH, SURE,
YOU TALK A BIG GAME,
BUT ALL ANY OF US HAVE ACTUALLY
SEEN YOU DO SO FAR IS PASS
A COUPLE OF UNDERPOWERED CARS
ON AN UPHILL STRAIGHTAWAY,
NOT EXACTLY SOMETHING
TO BRAG ABOUT.
- WAIT. WHAT ARE SAYING?
D'YOU THINK...
YOU REALLY THINK IT'D BE ANY
DIFFERENT ON A DOWNHILL RUN?
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
TAKE THAT ANY WAY YOU LIKE.
JUST LEAVE US ALONE, DICK.
YOU WANNA PEDDLE THAT B.S.
YOU AND YOUR SIDEKICK
DO IT ON YOUR OWN TURF.
- IF THAT'S HOW IT IS.
- ( engine revs )
- WHY DON'T I HAVE
A GOOD FEELING ABOUT THIS?
- BECAUSE THOSE IDIOTS
ARE GONNA AMBUSH US
THE SECOND WE TRY
TO DRIVE PAST THEM.
I GUESS WE MUST HAVE REALLY MADE
AN IMPRESSION ON THOSE JERKS,
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
OUT FOR BLOOD.
- C'MON, WHAT WERE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO?
LET THEM CRAP ALL OVER
OUR RIDE LIKE THAT
AND JUST STAND THERE
WITH SMILES ON OUR FACES?
- NO, OF COURSE NOT. IT'S TRUE,
MY BABY IS VERY SENSITIVE
BUT SHE'LL PULVERIZE THEM
ON THE DOWNHILL.
- I DON'T DOUBT IT. NOW
WHADDYA SAY WE SHOW THEM
WHAT KINDA DRIVERS
WE REALLY ARE?
- HELL YEAH!
- WHOA. WAIT A SEC.
YOU EXPECT ME TO
TAKE THESE GUYS ON ?
WELL, YOU CAN JUST FORGET IT.
I'M IN NO SHAPE TO RACE
ANYONE RIGHT NOW.
- IT'S NOT LIKE WE
CAN ASK PROJECT D
TO GET INVOLVED ON OUR BEHALF.
THEY WOULDN'T GIVE A LAME-ASS
RACE LIKE THIS THE TIME OF DAY.
- YEAH. YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
FINE THEN. I'LL BE THE ONE.
- ( exclaims )
AM I HEARING THIS? UNEXPECTED
DECISIVENESS FROM IKETANI?
- UNEXPECTED, HUH? YEAH.
I GUESS SO. LET'S PUT
SOME INSURANCE ON THIS.
- INSURANCE?
- ( engine running )
- IT GOES WITHOUT
SAYING THAT FORGIVENESS
IS OUT OF THE QUESTION.
I WAS TALKING SHOP
LIKE A GENTLEMAN
AND THEY HAD TO GO AND
GET ALL TWISTED.
WELL, THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHO THEY'VE CROSSED.
- HEADS UP, BOSS.
HERE THEY COME.
- OKAY TIME TO TAKE
YOUR MEDICINE.
- ( tires screeching )
- UPHILL OR DOWNHILL.
I'M GUARANTEED A WIN.
BECAUSE YEARS OF CIRCUIT-BASED
TRAINING AND TECHNIQUE
ALWAYS TRIUMPHS OVER
PISS-ANT STREETERS!
- BIG SHOCK, MAN. THEY'RE
CHASING US. HEADS UP!
- BRING IT ON. THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKIN' ABOUT.
THIS IS MY FIRST
BATTLE IN A WHILE.
- ( tires screeching )
- GUESS THE LOCAL SCENERY AROUND
HERE ISN'T TOO SHABBY AFTER ALL.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. THAT PIDDLY
LITTLE S-ONE-THREE CORNERS
BETTER THAN I EXPECTED IT WOULD.
BUT IT'S NO TROUBLE
TO STAY ON HIM.
IT HAS TO BE SAID EVEN
THIS EARLY ON
IT'S EASY TO TELL I'M
THE BETTER DRIVER.
IT FEELS LIKE I COULD OUTRUN
THE SPEED OF THOUGHT ITSELF.
( chuckles )
I'M SUCH A BADASS, IT HURTS!
- ( tires screeching )
- ( exclaiming )
HEY, I'M SORRY TO BREAK YOUR
CONCENTRATION AND ALL THAT,
BUT DO YOU MIND
IF I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- NAH, MAN. GO RIGHT AHEAD.
WHAT IS IT?
- I DUNNO, MAN, IT'S JUST...
DO YOU THINK A
TURBO-FITTED EIGHT-FIVE
WOULD REALLY BE AS USELESS
ON A CIRCUIT RACE
AS THAT FAT BASTARD
SAID IT WOULD?
- I DUNNO ABOUT THAT.
LIKE I TOLD YOU DRIVING
IT'S GONNA TAKE
SOME GETTING USED TO FOR ME
NOW THERE'S SO MUCH MORE TORQUE,
BUT IT'S WHATEVER, RIGHT?
THIS IS YOUR CAR, DUDE.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
HAVING CONFIDENCE
IN YOUR OWN RIDE
IS WHAT RACING IS ALL ABOUT.
- I THOUGHT MY CAR
WOULD BE FASTER,
I HAD NO IDEA, IT
WOULD BE LIKE THIS.
- THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
IKETANI CAN'T HOLD THE LEAD.
- HUH?
- YOU CAN TELL BY THE WAY
HE TAKES THESE CORNERS
HE KNOWS THIS COURSE LIKE
THE BACK OF HIS HAND.
BUT FROM WHAT I CAN TELL BACK
HERE, FATASS HAS BETTER TRACTION
HE GETS OUT OF THE SAME
CORNERS WITH WAY BETTER BALANCE
BUT THE DIFFERENCE ISN'T
IN THEIR DRIVING TECHNIQUE
WHEN YOU GET RIGHT DOWN TO IT.
IT REALLY ALL COMES DOWN
TO THEIR CARS.
- WHO THE HECK ARE YOU AND WHAT
HAVE YOU DONE WITH TAKUMI?
THERE'S NO WAY
HE'S THE TAKUMI I KNOW.
THE WORDS COMING OUT
OF HIS MOUTH ARE BITCHIN.
- CHECK IT OUT, MAN.
IKETANI'S ABOUT TO GET DUSTED.
- FOR REAL?
- ON THE STRAIGHTAWAY
AFTER THIS CORNER.
- SON OF A BITCH.
WE'RE NOT DONE.
- HA, HA! SEE? YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT YOU GET, DILL WEED!
THINK YOU STILL HAVE A CHANCE?
SEE WHAT YOU THINK AFTER SOME
FREE-BRAKING, CIRCUIT-STYLE.
LET'S SEE HOW THEY
LIKE THEM APPLES.
TRY CORNERING AFTER HAVING
TO BRAKE LIKE THAT,
YOU COCKY S.O.B.
THAT'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
WE IN THE KNOW LIKE TO CALL
TAKING THE KIDS TO SCHOOL.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
HE'S RIGHT ON OUR ASS!
- I DON'T BELIEVE THAT INSOLENT
LITTLE PIECE OF CRAP.
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE
ME DOWN WITH AN S-1-3,
THEN YOU'VE GOT
ANOTHER THING COMING!
- I CAN'T EVEN KEEP UP
WITH HIM.
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
THE EIGHT-FIVE CAN.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( gasps ) I DON'T GET IT.
I THOUGHT THERE WAS MORE
DISTANCE BETWEEN US.
HE'S PRACTICALLY IN MY TRUNK!
RIDICULOUS! MY FLAWLESS
CIRCUIT-BASED TECHNIQUE
IS LOSING TO SOME CORN-FED,
MOUNTAIN-PASS STREETER!
NO, NO. I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I WON'T BELIEVE IT!
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING!
- HEY, WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
THAT'S NOT THE S-ONE-THREE
BEHIND US NOW.
I THINK THAT'S THE CAR...
- WOULD YOU SHUT THE HELL UP?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO CONCENTRATE
WITH YOU JABBERING IN MY EAR.
I NEED ALL THE FOCUS I CAN GET.
- AH, SO YOU'RE GONNA DO THAT.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
( exhales )
MY MIND AND THE ROAD
BEFORE ME MUST BE AS ONE.
WAIT FOR IT. WAIT FOR IT.
NOT YET.
SEIZE THE DAY!
HOPE YOU'RE READY TO EAT DUST,
YOU STREETER PUNKS!
SECRET WEAPON. MY ULTRA-MEGA
LATE-BRAKING STYLE!
( gasps )
- ( both screaming )
- ( both scream )
- OH NO! HOLY CRAP! DUDE,
HANG ON TO SOMETHIN'!
WE'RE GONNA CRASH!
- ( laughs )
- I'D HAVE GIVEN ANYTHING
TO SEE THE LOOK
ON THAT FAT BASTARD'S FACE...
GOOD THING WE HAD
INSURANCE, HUH?
- AIN'T THAT THE TRUTH?
( laughs )
- MAN, IT'S CRAZY HOW
AWESOME TAKUMI'S GOTTEN
EVER SINCE THE BIG D
RECRUITED HIM, ISN'T IT?
- YOU'RE RIGHT, HE SEEMS
LIKE A NEW MAN.
I MEAN THE WAY HE WAS HANDLING
THE EIGHT-FIVE OUT THERE
LAST NIGHT WAS GENIUS,
PURE AND SIMPLE.
HELL, YOU'D HAVE GIVEN ANYTHING
TO SEE THE LOOK ON HIS
FACE, BELIEVE ME.
BEHIND THE WHEEL, HE WAS LIKE
SOME KIND OF ICE SCULPTURE.
DUDE DIDN'T EVEN BREAK A SWEAT.
- PART OF WHY HE'S SO GOOD NOW
IS 'CAUSE HE KNOWS HOW
TO KEEP IT COOL UNDER PRESSURE.
- BETWEEN HEARING ABOUT
THESE OTHER GUYS HE'S BEATEN
AND SEEING HIM IN ACTION
FOR MYSELF, I GOTTA TELL YA,
I DON'T THINK WE'LL
EVER SEE ANYONE
BEAT TAKUMI ON AKINA'S DOWNHILL.
- ( chuckles)
I'D PUT MONEY ON THAT.
- HEY, MASASHI? YEAH, LET'S GO
FOR IT. I LIKE WHAT I'VE SEEN.
I KNOW. I HAD DOUBTS ABOUT
THAT ONE AT FIRST, TOO, BUT
GUESS YOU COULD SAY,
THAT IT JUST FELT RIGHT.
TOOLIN' AROUND IN THAT THING
WAS EXACTLY WHAT I NEEDED.
I'LL GET THE
PAPERWORK TOGETHER
AND HEAD OVER TO YOUR
PLACE IN A BIT.
- ( engine revving )
- Woman: I'M NOT
KIDDING, WE MUST BE
ON THE PHONE WITH EACH OTHER
AT LEAST THREE HOURS A NIGHT.
THE PHONE BILL'S
TOTALLY KILLING ME.
IT IS SO WORTH IT, THOUGH.
EARTH TO KYOKO.
YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
- YEAH, I'M LISTENING.
- WHATEVER. YOU WERE THINKING
ABOUT CARS AGAIN, WEREN'T YOU?
IT'S ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET A MAN
IF KEEP BEING SUCH A TOMBOY.
- MAYBE I DON'T CARE
ABOUT GETTING A MAN
UNLESS HE CAN RESPECT ME
FOR WHO I AM.
YOU EVER THINK ABOUT THAT?
GUYS OVER CARS?
C'MON, THERE'S NO CONTEST.
DATING IS FOR PEOPLE WHO
DON'T HAVE BETTER THINGS
TO DO WITH THEIR TIME.
NO THANKS.
- STOP IT. YOU MUST
HAVE A FANTASY GUY.
- YEAH WELL. MAYBE I DO.
BUT HE DRIVES A ROTARY, AND
HE'S FASTER THAN ME.
NO EASY ACCOMPLISHMENT
IN REAL LIFE, I GUARANTEE YOU.
PLUS, I'D NEVER EVEN CONSIDER
DATING SOMEONE
WHO DIDN'T LOOK AS BADASS BEHIND
THE WHEEL OF AN FD AS I DO.
- 'KAY, JUST SO YOU'RE AWARE,
GUYS ARE PUT OFF BY
THAT KINDA TALK.
- BUT, YOU NEVER KNOW,
MY MR. RIGHT MIGHT BE OUT
THERE SOMEWHERE
'COURSE I WOULDN'T BET ON IT.
- SORRY ABOUT THIS, KEISUKE.
USUALLY IT'S KENTA'S JOB TO
SCOUT OUT THE COURSE FOR US,
BUT HE WASN'T ABLE
TO GET OUT OF WORK TODAY.
- IT'S COOL, MAN.
I HAD NOTHING BETTER TO DO.
- ( birds chirping )
- HUH?
- THAT GIRL LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S LOOKING FOR SOMETHING.
YOU THINK THAT CELL PHONE
YOU FOUND BELONGS TO HER?
- LOSE SOMETHING?
- HUH?
- BECAUSE IF I HAD
TO TAKE A GUESS,
I'D SAY YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A
SILVER CELL PHONE. AM I RIGHT?
- AS A MATTER OF FACT, YOU ARE.
- I FOUND ONE ON THE EDGE
OF THE PARKING LOT A WHILE AGO
AND I ASKED THE PEOPLE THAT RUN
THAT STORE TO HOLD ON TO IT
IN CASE THE OWNER CAME BACK.
- THANKS. I'M SUCH
A KLUTZ WITH THAT THING.
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME
I'VE LOST IT, EITHER.
I USUALLY JUST STICK THE PHONE
ON THE INSIDE OF MY CAR DOOR
WHILE I'M DRIVING,
SO, WHEN I GET OUT
THE STUPID THING FALLS.
I WAS HERE PRETTY LATE
LAST NIGHT AND IT WAS DARK.
SO, UM...
- NO, I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY GO
INSIDE AND GET IT.
- RIGHT.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M NOT
DREAMING THIS.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S GORGEOUS AND THAT RIDE!
OKAY, I'M MIGHT BE
GOING CRAZY, BUT
I THINK I'VE JUST MET
MY MR. RIGHT!
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ WHO YOU WANNA BE,
WHO YOU WANNA BE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA SEE,
WHAT YOU WANNA SEE ♪
♪ NEW GENERATION ♪
♪ THIS WILL BLAST YOUR LOVE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
BREAK OFF THE BARRIER ♪
♪ BLAST MY DESIRE,
STRONGER THAN FIRE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪
♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BLAST MY DESIRE ♪
- ♪ BE WHAT YOU WANNA BE ♪
- ♪ BREAK WHAT YOU WANNA BREAK ♪