- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ( engine revving )
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU'RE NOT PULLIN' AWAY
FROM ME AGAIN.
I WON'T LET YOU.
NOT UNTIL I'VE HAD A CHANCE
TO COUNTER-ATTACK!
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
THE PROBABILITY TAKUMI IS GONNA
TRY THE OBVIOUS KYOICHI TACTIC?
- Ryosuke: PRETTY HIGH.
HE'LL REALIZE
SOON ENOUGH HOW USELESS
THAT APPROACH WOULD BE, THOUGH.
LET'S JUST HOPE IT'S SOON ENOUGH
TO MATTER.
- ( upbeat music playing )
- ♪ INTO THE GROOVE, BOY ♪
♪ AND YOU GOT TO PROVE, GIRL ♪
♪ GOT NOTHING TO LOSE NOW ♪
♪ WE STEP ONTO THE BEAT ♪
♪ GET ON YOUR FEET, BOY ♪
♪ AND STEPS TO THE BEAT, GIRL ♪
♪ TOGETHER AND HIP NOW ♪
♪ YOU LET THE MUSIC ♪
♪ SET ME FREE ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO KNOW ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE SPECIAL ♪
♪ YOU'RE MOVING ROUND ♪
♪ AND ROUND AND ROUND ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE SO SEXUAL ♪
♪ SEXY BABY ♪
♪ ANOTHER NIGHT, BABY ♪
♪ MOVING UP, MOVING NOW ♪
♪ I SEE THE FIRE BURNING UP ♪
♪ BURNING UP ♪
- NO! HOW'S HE ABLE
TO STAY ON ME LIKE THIS?
HE'S FOLLOWIN' MY LINE
EVEN WITH ALL THE SPRAY
COMIN' OFF MY TIRES,
NOT TO MENTION
IT'S FRIGGIN' DARK.
OKAY, JUST CALM DOWN.
GET A GRIP, DUDE.
LOSE YOUR COOL NOW AND YOU COULD
LOSE YOUR LIFE IN THIS SHIT.
SO WHAT IF HE'S RIDIN' MY ASS?
THERE'S NO WAY HE CAN PASS ME.
I'M A RALLYIST! NOW, COME ON!
♪ BURNING UP, BURNING UP ♪
- MAN, VISIBILITY IS CRAP
'CAUSE OF THIS SPRAY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I COULDN'T CARE LESS.
- YOU RECALL THAT BLIND
ATTACK TAKUMI PULLED OFF
IN THE FINAL ROUND AGAINST
THE TOUDOU SCHOOL?
- SURE. IT'S NOT LIKE
THAT'S SOMETHING
A GUY CAN JUST FORGET, YOU KNOW.
HE DROVE WITH HIS LIGHTS OFF
ON A MOUNTAIN PASS.
- YEAH, WELL, THE GENIUS BEHIND
THAT LITTLE MOVE,
IT'S THAT MINDSET THAT'S GONNA
SAVE HIM OUT THERE TONIGHT.
- HOW'S THAT EXACTLY?
- TAKUMI'S ABLE TO WORK
OFF AN IMAGE HE'S GOT
OF THE COURSE IN HIS HEAD.
EVEN WITH VISIBILITY
AT NEAR-ZERO
HE CAN NAVIGATE IT FROM MEMORY.
HE'S ONE OF A KIND.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THE WAY
HE CAN VISUALIZE A COURSE.
SO LONG AS HE CAN ACCURATELY
GAUGE HIS OPPONENT'S SPEED,
HE CAN FOLLOW THEIR LINE.
UNDER ANY CONDITIONS.
ONE OF TAKUMI'S GREATEST ASSETS
IS HIS ABILITY TO FEEL THE ROAD
EVEN WHEN HE CAN'T SEE IT.
AND THAT'S WHAT SETS HIM
APART FROM OTHER DRIVERS.
- WHAT? HE'S STILL ON HIM?
ARE YOU SHITTIN' ME?
- TELL ME WHERE THEY ARE.
THEY'RE OVER ON THE S-CURVES.
RIGHT ABOUT MIDWAY THROUGH.
AT THIS RATE, WE WON'T
GET 'EM IN JUST ONE RUN.
- THAT WOULD BE UNFORTUNATE.
I WASN'T PREPARED FOR SAKAMOTO
TO LOSE.
I HAVE TO START THINKING OF A
STRATEGY FOR THE SECOND RUN
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- WAIT, YOU MEAN FOR WHEN
THE CAPPUCCINO IS LIKE, CHASING?
- THIS IS NOT GOOD.
FOR STARTERS, I HADN'T THOUGHT
THERE'D BE A SECOND RUN.
CAN IT BE THE RAIN?
SAKAMOTO HAS ONLY BEEN
DRIVING THE CAPPUCCINO
FOR THE PAST WEEK OR SO,
AND TO WATCH OUR OPPONENT DRIVE,
YOU'D ALMOST THINK
HE AND THAT EIGHT-SIX CAME
OFF THE SAME ASSEMBLY LINE.
IF ONLY THE COURSE WERE DRY.
DAMN IT.
I NEVER THOUGHT IT POSSIBLE,
BUT HE'S PLAYING OUR OWN
ACE AGAINST US!
- ( engines revving )
- I DON'T LIKE THIS
ONE DAMN BIT.
HE'S ABOUT TO TRY
AND MAKE A MOVE.
I KNOW HE IS.
I CAN FEEL IT.
WHAT'S HE THINKIN'?
EVEN WITHOUT THE RAIN THE
CORNER'D BE TOO NARROW.
DON'T SCREW WITH ME, MAN!
JUST STAY BACK THERE ALL
NICE AND QUIET.
LIKE A GOOD LITTLE LOSER.
- THAT'S IT!
- WHAT?
DIDN'T I TELL YOU NOT TO SCREW
WITH ME, YOU LITTLE BITCH?
- DAMN, NO GOOD!
- JUST LIKE I THOUGHT.
HOW CAN I COUNTER-ATTACK
ON SOMEONE
WHO CORNERS FASTER THAN ME?
OKAY. I'VE ONLY GOT TIME LEFT
FOR ONE MORE SHOT!
THERE'S A FEW MORE CORNERS
COMIN' UP.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
AN IN SOMEWHERE.
THE NEXT ONE'LL BE MY LAST TRY.
IF RYOSUKE THINKS I CAN DO IT,
I KNOW I CAN TAKE
THIS SON OF A BITCH DOWN!
- IT WON'T BE
MUCH LONGER NOW, HUH?
- I GUESS NOT. YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S ONE NIGHT
I'M NOT EVER GONNA FORGET.
WHEN TAKUMI PASSED ME.
I'D NEVER BEEN SO SHOCKED
IN MY LIFE.
- ( rain pattering )
- ( engine revving )
- I DON'T GIVE A CRAP IF
LIGHTWEIGHT BEATS FINE-TUNING.
HE'S NOT GONNA LOSE.
NOT TO THIS JACKASS, ANYWAY.
AND NOT 'CAUSE OF THE RAIN.
- ( tires screeching )
- GO FOR IT!
- SERIOUSLY? NOW?
HEY, IT'S YOUR FUNERAL, DUDE!
- I'M GOING IN!
- OH, MAN. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED BACK THERE,
BUT THAT WAS WAY TOO CLOSE.
GREAT. HE'S MANAGED TO PULL AWAY
FROM ME AGAIN.
SO A COUNTER-ATTACK
WON'T WORK AFTER ALL.
STILL...
- THINK ABOUT KYOICHI SUTO,
HE AND THE EMPERORS,
HOW DO YOU THINK THEY COPE WITH
MESSY CONDITIONS LIKE THESE?
THAT'LL BE
THE KEY TO YOUR STRATEGY.
AND BEAR IN MIND THE POINT
HERE IS TO DO THE OPPOSITE
OF WHAT YOU'D NORMALLY DO.
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW HAS TO
BE LOOKED AT IN REVERSE.
- I STILL DON'T GET IT.
IF HE DOESN'T MEAN A
KYOICHI-STYLE COUNTER-ATTACK,
WHAT DOES HE MEAN?
- YES, THANK YOU. I UNDERSTAND.
YOU WERE RIGHT WHEN
YOU SAID MY ADVICE
WAS A LITTLE ABSTRACT EARLIER,
BUT IF HE CAN HOLD HIS OWN WITH
THE CAPPUCCINO FOR THIS LONG,
CHANCES ARE HE UNDERSTANDS.
THE BASIC POINT, AT LEAST.
ENOUGH TO GUIDE HIM
PROVIDED HE KNOWS HIMSELF.
- YEAH. BUT HOW WELL
DOES HE KNOW HIMSELF?
- HE'LL BE FINE IF
HE CAN KEEP UP
WHILE NEGOTIATING THE FIRST
AND MIDDLE SECTIONS.
THOSE ARE BY FAR THE TOUGHEST
SEGMENTS OF THE COURSE.
- SO WHERE HE SHOULD
MAKE HIS MOVE...
- EXACTLY. THE LAST STRETCH.
OVERTAKING THE OTHER GUY
WHERE BEING LIGHTWEIGHT
NO LONGER MAKES AN IOTA
OF DIFFERENCE.
- YEAH.
- KYOICHI AND HIS GANG
WOULDN'T HESITATE
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THAT.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, THEY WOULDN'T.
AND THAT'S BY FAR
THE SAFEST PLACE
WHERE HE COULD TRY TO PASS.
- HMM. THE TRICK'LL
BE WHETHER OR NOT
THE SAFEST WAY IS
THE MOST OBVIOUS.
TAKUMI MAY HAVE TO WIDEN HIS
NOTION OF FAIR PLAY SOMEWHAT
TO TAKE THAT LEAP.
- FREAKIN' PERFECT.
THE LEVEL STRAIGHTAWAY WE'RE
COMIN' UP ON SOON
IS GONNA BE MY BIGGEST HEADACHE.
I AM NOT GONNA LET THIS CRAZY
BASTARD PASS ME!
I DON'T CARE WHAT I'VE GOTTA
PULL OUT OF MY ASS.
I'M DRAGGING THIS
INTO A SECOND RUN!
- I HADN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT THE STRAIGHTAWAY
RIGHT BEFORE THE FINISH.
IF I WANTED TO PASS HIM,
THAT'D BE MY BEST SHOT.
BUT SOMETHING'S NAGGIN' AT ME.
I MEAN, PASSING ON A
STRAIGHTAWAY AFTER LOSING TWICE
AT THE CORNERS?
CAN YOU EVEN
CALL THAT A VICTORY?
AND WOULD RYOSUKE
WANT ME TO DO THAT?
HELL IF I KNOW. THERE'S NO
POINT IN WAFFLIN' NOW.
YOU HAVEN'T GOT TIME.
BUT I DON'T KNOW!
SHOULD I DO THIS OR NOT?
ARE YOU GONNA LET THIS JERK
DRAG US INTO A SECOND RUN?
COME ON, MAN, THINK!
- OKAY, IS HE GONNA COME AT ME
FROM THE RIGHT OR THE LEFT?
MAN. FOR MAINTAINING THE LEAD
ON A STRAIGHTAWAY,
THE SIZE OF THIS THING
IS WORTHLESS.
EVEN IF I KEEP TO THE MIDDLE,
THERE'S TOO MUCH ROOM
ON EITHER SIDE OF ME.
I DON'T WANNA DO THIS, DUDE,
BELIEVE ME.
BUT I'LL BE DAMNED
IF I'M GONNA GIVE YOU AN IN!
- WHICH IS IT? SHOULD I
MAKE A GO AT THIS OR NOT?
WHAT WOULD RYOSUKE
WANT ME TO DO?
- LEFT IT IS!
YOU ARE NOT GETTING
IN FRONT OF ME, PUNK!
NOBODY MESSES WITH A RALLYIST
AND LIVES TO TELL ABOUT IT!
- OKAY. YOU'RE WILLING TO GO
THAT FAR, HUH?
WELL, IN THAT CASE...
- HEY! I CAN TOTALLY SEE THEM,
YOU GUYS! CHECK IT OUT!
HERE THEY COME!
- ( tires screeching )
- HOLY CRAP!
- OH, MAN! THE EIGHT-SIX
JUST FREAKIN' VANISHED!
- YOU'RE IN FOR A RUDE AWAKENING
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN
CARRY THIS OVER INTO
ANOTHER RUN, TAKUMI.
DON'T GET HUNG UP
ON A CLEAN VICTORY.
IF STYLE MEANS SO MUCH TO YOU
YOU'RE WILLING TO LOSE,
THIS ISN'T THE GAME FOR YOU,
MY FRIEND.
WHAT DOESN'T GET US
OVER THAT FINISH LINE FIRST,
WE JUST GOTTA LEARN TO IGNORE.
IF YOU MISS YOUR CHANCE
TO PASS THIS GUY,
I KNOW IT'S NOT
'CAUSE YOU CAN'T.
IT'S 'CAUSE YOU WON'T.
STYLE IS WHAT YOU MAKE IT.
YOU CAN DO THIS, TAKUMI!
WIN IT!
- WHERE'D HE GO?
HE JUST FRIGGIN' DISAPPEAR?
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
HIS HEADLIGHTS WERE PRACTICALLY
IN MY TRUNK A SECOND AGO,
WEREN'T THEY?
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
- ( revving )
WHAT THE HELL?
- ♪ I BELIEVE IN LOVIN' YOU ♪
♪ I BELIEVE IN LOVIN' YOU ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
I DO.
( screaming )
♪ I'M YOUR LOVER ♪
♪ DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT TO TALK IT OVER ♪
- SAKAMOTO JUST GOT PASSED,
MAN. THE EIGHT-SIX WON IT.
- IMPOSSIBLE. HOW COULD HE HAVE
ENDED IT IN A SINGLE RUN?
- ♪ I WILL SHOW THE WORLD ♪
♪ I MEAN IT ALL THE WAY ♪
♪ I BELIEVE IN LOVIN' YOU ♪
♪ AND I BELIEVE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE IS TRUE ♪
- I TOLD YOU, DIDN'T?
YOU'D HAVE TO THINK
DIFFERENTLY ABOUT YOURSELF.
THE FIRST AND ONLY
THING A DRIVER
SHOULD CONCERN HIMSELF
WITH IS WHETHER OR NOT
HE CAN MAXIMIZE THE
POTENTIAL OF HIS VEHICLE.
WHEN IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE,
THERE'S REALLY NOTHING MORE
TO IT THAN THAT.
IF DURING A RACE YOU FIND
SOMETHING ABOUT YOUR CAR
THAT'S JUST PLAIN BETTER
THAN THE ONE YOUR OPPONENT
IS BEHIND THE WHEEL OF,
WELL, THEN THINK ABOUT IT,
AND NINE TIMES OUT OF TEN
THAT'LL BE YOUR INROAD.
TECHNIQUE IS THERE TO LEARN
HOW TO TRANSCEND IT.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED YOU
TO WALK AWAY WITH TONIGHT.
WHEN I TOLD YOU TO THINK LIKE
KYOICHI I DIDN'T MEAN FOR YOU
TO EMULATE HIS TACTICS
OR TRY TO PULL OFF ONE OF HIS
SIGNATURE COUNTER-ATTACKS.
I WANTED YOU TO REALLY
GET INSIDE HIS HEAD.
THAT SAID, OF COURSE, MOST OF
YOUR BATTLE TONIGHT WAS DECIDED
IN THE FIRST HALF ANYWAY.
I'M IMPRESSED YOU STAYED ON
THE CAPPUCINO'S TAIL. GOOD JOB.
YOU CAN REST FOR NOW. THE TIMED
TRIAL HAS BEEN CANCELED.
- HELL OF A RACE, MAN.
- HE DID MEAN THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT, RIGHT?
- ( chuckling )
- TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
I'M KINDA HAVING TROUBLE
COMING TO TERMS WITH IT.
I KNOW I HAD TO PASS HIM
LIKE THAT TO PULL THE WIN,
BUT IT DIDN'T FEEL RIGHT.
IT TOOK ME SO LONG TO FIGURE OUT
I ALMOST LOST THE RACE.
AND I THOUGHT ABOUT JUST HOLDIN'
OFF AND WAITIN' ON A SECOND RUN.
- WELL, IT'S A DAMN GOOD THING
YOU DIDN'T DO THAT.
IF YOU HADN'T MADE YOUR MOVE
WHEN YOU DID,
RYOSUKE WOULD'VE TORN YOU
A NEW ONE FOR SURE.
- HUH? YOU... YOU THINK SO?
- I KNOW SO. THERE'S NO
GUARANTEE THE RAIN
WOULD'VE LASTED THROUGH
ANOTHER RUN, NOW WAS THERE?
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
THE WEATHER IS WHAT HAD
YOUR BACK TONIGHT.
IF THE ROAD HAD BEEN DRY,
THAT PINK PIECE OF CRAP
WOULD'VE WIPED THE ROAD
WITH YOU. NO CONTEST.
- OKAY. YEAH.
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- KEEP IN MIND, IF THIS WAS
YOUR OWN PERSONAL BATTLE,
YOU COULD'VE DONE WHATEVER
YOU DAMN WELL PLEASED OUT THERE.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE
RACING FOR PROJECT D,
YOU'RE DEFENDING ALL
OUR REPUTATIONS.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
- MAN! I DON'T BELIEVE
THIS CRAP!
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED
TO YOU OUT THERE, DUDE?
HOW DO YOU GET BEATEN
BY AN EIGHT-SIX, SERIOUSLY?
WE HAD THIS THING
IN THE GODDAMN BAG!
WHAT DO YOU
HAVE TO SAY FOR YOURSELF?
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW.
THE WHOLE SITUATION
THROWS ME, OKAY?
ONE MINUTE I CAN SEE HIM IN MY
REARVIEW MIRROR, AND THE NEXT,
HE'S FRIGGIN' GONE
LIKE SOME SORT OF GHOST.
- YOU SAY HE DISAPPEARED,
BUT SURELY THE GUY WAS JUST
DRIVING IN YOUR BLIND SPOT?
- I'D HAVE SEEN HIM
MOVE INTO IT, THOUGH.
BY THE TIME I REALIZED
WHAT WAS HAPPENING,
HE WAS ALREADY
RIGHT ALONGSIDE ME.
- BY THE TIME YOU REALIZED
HE HAD YOUR ASS YOU MEAN.
START TALKING SENSE,
'CAUSE NOBODY CAN JUST UP
AND DISAPPEAR.
- THEN YOU PUT IT HOWEVER
YOU WANT TO.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN
WHAT I DON'T GET.
BELIEVE ME, NO ONE'S MORE
SHOCKED ABOUT THIS THAN ME.
- WELL, YEAH. I'M JUST SAYIN'.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE EITHER ONE
OF YOU HAD ANY BETTER LUCK
AGAINST THE EIGHT-SIX, RIGHT?
I'VE HAD ABOUT ALL OF THIS
I CAN TAKE.
I JUST HOPE THE OTHER RALLY
DRIVERS DON'T HEAR ABOUT THIS.
NO TELLIN' HOW LONG IT'LL TAKE
FOR ME TO GET OVER IT.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
THERE'S JUST SOMETHIN'
DIFFERENT ABOUT THAT GUY.
IT'S LIKE HE'S NOT EVEN HUMAN.
- ANY WAY YOU SLICE IT,
A BLIND ATTACK IN THE RAIN
WAS ONE HELL OF
AN EFFECTIVE TACTIC.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH TO
SEE COMIN' AT YOU
UNDER THE BEST OF CONDITIONS.
SO TO HIM IT MUST'VE LOOKED
LIKE YOU VANISHED INTO THIN AIR.
IT'S A POWERFUL TOOL TO HAVE
UNDER YOUR BELT IN A DOGFIGHT.
RYOSUKE THINKS SO, TOO.
- YEAH, MAYBE IT IS,
BUT I DON'T WANNA USE IT OFTEN.
THIS MAY SOUND STRANGE,
BUT BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
I JUST DON'T LIKE
THE WAY IT FEELS.
IT'S TOO MUCH OF AN EASY OUT,
YOU KNOW?
- YOU CALL PULLIN' OFF
THAT KINDA MOVE EASY?
- WELL, YEAH. LIKE A REFLEX,
I GUESS.
IT'LL KINDA HIT ME
OUT OF THE BLUE,
LIKE WHEN MY OPPONENT
WON'T OPEN UP A PATH FOR ME,
OR MAYBE JUST WHEN I GET
REALLY PISSED OFF OR SOMETHIN'.
I DON'T KNOW.
- THERE'S OUR CHAMPION!
HEY, TAKUMI!
DUDE! YOU WERE SO THAT GUY'S
WORST NIGHTMARE!
OF COURSE, YOU TOTALLY SCARED
THE BE-JESUS OUTTA US.
WE LOST SIGHT OF YOU
THERE FOR A SEC.
- HE'S RIGHT.
IT WAS THE DAMNEDEST THING.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
( chuckling )
- YOU NEARLY RAN OVER
YOUR THREE BEST FRIENDS,
BUT WE FORGIVE YA,
SEEIN' AS HOW YOU'RE A
COMPLETE GOD. ( laughing )
- NEXT TIME, MAYBE
TRY NOT STANDING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE ROAD.
- ( car starting )
- WAIT. HEY, IS THAT...
- ( revving )
- THAT LEVIN! COULD IT BE...
THAT BABY BELONGS TO WATARU!
- WELL, YEAH.
YOU JUST NOW NOTICED?
HE'S REPRESENTING OUR
OPPONENTS IN THE HILL CLIMB
ABOUT TO HAPPEN HERE
IN A LITTLE BIT.
- ( explosion )
- ( screaming )
- WHAT? BUT IF WATARU'S AROUND,
THAT MEANS SHE MIGHT BE TOO!
K... KAZUMI IS HERE?
- ( heart beating loudly )
- KAZUMI!
- HUH?
- ( spluttering )
DO YOU REMEMBER ME?
( spluttering nervously )
- ITSUKI, HEY!
- A COMPRESSOR, HUH?
YOU SWITCHED OVER TO
A SUPER-CHARGER?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
AFTER LOSING TO THE TRUENO
LAST FALL, IT OCCURRED TO ME.
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY
THE TURBO AND ME
DECIDED TO GO OUR SEPARATE WAYS.
THE ENGINE WAS GIVIN' ME
MORE GRIEF THAN IT WAS WORTH,
SO I CAME UP WITH A
PRETTY DECENT SOLUTION
IF I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
THE KIND OF IMMEDIATE RESPONSE
YOU GET FROM A SUPER-CHARGER
ISN'T ALL THAT DIFFERENT
FROM AN NA.
BUT YOU DON'T GET ALL THE
NIT-PICKY B.S. WITH THIS PUPPY
LIKE YOU DO WITH TURBO, SO IT'S
A LOT LIKE SWITCHING OVER
TO A LARGE DISPLACEMENT ENGINE.
AND DAMN NEAR PERFECT
FOR THE TYPE OF COURSE
YOU AND I ARE GONNA RUN TONIGHT.
KEEP THAT IN MIND
WHEN YOU SEE MY TAIL LIGHTS.
- OKAY, I GET IT. SO THAT'S HOW
IT'S GONNA BE. TELL YOU WHAT.
IF YOU WANNA LEARN
HOW TO DRIVE A TURBO,
THEN JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
- LINE 'EM UP, PEOPLE!
THE LEVIN OUT FRONT
WITH THE FD CHASING.
- YOUR OBJECTIVE THIS TIME
IS THE SAME AS LAST WEEK'S.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
THE ROAD CONDITIONS TONIGHT
WILL BE VIRTUALLY THE SAME
AS THEY WERE FOR THAT RACE.
-OKAY, BRO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
YOU GUYS JUST WATCH ME
DO MY THING, ALL RIGHT?
- FINE.
♪ GO, GO, GO, GO ♪
- ( upbeat music playing )
- ( engine revving )
- EVERYBODY READY?
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
STARTING IN FIVE... FOUR...
THREE... TWO...
ONE... GO!
- OH, WOW! WATARU'S LEVIN
JUST PUSHED OFF
WITH AS MUCH POWER
AS KEISUKE'S FD!
UN-FREAKIN'-BELIEVABLE!
I JUST HAD A TURBO INSTALLED IN
MY LEVIN, TOO, BUT I MEAN, DAMN!
- OH, THE OLD TURBO IS HISTORY.
HE'S HAD THAT PUPPY OUTFITTED
WITH A SUPER-CHARGER.
- HE'S GOT A SUPER-CHARGER?
- YEAH. HE BLEW OUT
THE OLD ENGINE
TRYING TO BEAT YOUR
FRIEND ON AKAGI.
MAN, I'D NEVER SEEN
WATARU SO TICKED OFF BEFORE.
THAT BATTLE REALLY GOT TO HIM.
AND THE POOR GUY
HAS BEEN DRIVIN'
LIKE A MAN POSSESSED EVER SINCE.
- YEAH. TAKUMI'LL
DO THAT TO YA.
STILL, I MEAN, A SUPER-CHARGER?
THAT'S GOIN' A BIT OVERBOARD,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- MAYBE. BUT YOU DO GOTTA ADMIT
IT IS A PRETTY GOOD MATCH
FOR A BEAST LIKE THE EIGHT-SIX
YOUR BUDDY, TAKUMI, DRIVES.
- YEAH.
- HEY, THE IMPORTANT THING IS
BRO'S SATISFIED.
HE'S SAYIN' HIS LEVIN HAS
MORE HORSEPOWER NOW
THAN THE TURBO EVER GAVE IT.
- ♪ I'VE GOT THE FIRE, BABY ♪
♪ I'M GONNA FIGHT ♪
♪ GET YOU READY, MY LADY ♪
♪ THIS NIGHT ♪
♪ WANNA TAKE YOU HIGHER ♪
♪ WANT TO PUSH YOUR LIFE ♪
- ONCE WE GET TO THE SECTIONS
COMIN' UP AHEAD,
DOESN'T MATTER HOW MUCH TORQUE
YOU'VE GOT IN THAT THING.
NO WAY
YOU'RE KEEPING UP WITH ME!
GET READY
TO EAT YOUR WORDS, PAL.
'CAUSE THIS RACE ISN'T GONNA BE
CAR AGAINST CAR.
IT'LL BE DRIVER AGAINST DRIVER!
- ( Nobody Reason playing )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
( rapping in Japanese )
♪ HATES AND PAIN ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ FOR THE REASON
THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
- ( continues singing
in Japanese )
- ♪ ALL AROUND THE WORLD ♪
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪
( singing in Japanese )