- ( theme song playing )
♪ WE'RE BACK ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( rapping in Japanese )
♪ I'M THE NOIZY TRIBE ♪
- ANY PREDICTIONS YET?
WHAT SHOULD WE BE ON THE
LOOKOUT FOR?
- I COULDN'T REALLY SAY
FOR SURE.
BUT IT'D SUCK TO BE
KEISUKE RIGHT NOW.
- HUH? WAIT... SERIOUSLY?
IS IT A TOUGH DOWNHILL?
I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS TOO BAD.
- NO. THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN...
OK, HOW SHOULD I PUT THIS?
TUNING YOUR CAR TO TACKLE A HILL
CLIMB IS GOOD AND ALL...
BUT SOONER OR LATER
YOUR GONNA HAVE TO
COME BACK DOWN THE
MOUNTAIN, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- BUT UNLIKE OTHERS WITH THAT
KIND OF TUNING...
KEISUKE'S SKILLS AREN'T LIMITED
TO HILL CLIMBING
BECAUSE LATELY HE'S BEEN
DRIVING DOWNHILL
JUST AS MUCH AS HE'S BEEN
DRIVING UPHILL.
- THEN THE SAME OUGHT BE
TRUE FOR YOU THEN, AM I RIGHT?
- WELL... THERE'S A BIG
DIFFERENCE IN HORSE POWER.
IF WE WERE ON A HILL CLIMB,
THE FD WOULD HAVE THE ADVANTAGE
OVER THE EIGHT-SIX,
HANDS DOWN.
DOWNHILL... HELL, EVEN THEN
THE FD WOULD PROBABLY
GIVE ME A
RUN FOR MY MONEY.
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED, THERE'S
NOT MUCH DIFFERENCE BETWEEN ME
AND KEISUKE WHEN WE'RE
ON THE ROAD.
- REALLY, I HAD NO IDEA.
- KEEP AN EYE ON HIM DURING
PRACTICE SOME TIME,
AND YOU'LL SEE WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
I MEAN I'M GLAD HE'S
IMPROVING AND ALL...
BUT I CAN'T SAY I'M EXACTLY
THRILLED ABOUT IT.
IN FACT, I'M KINDA GETTING
FREAKED OUT.
IF KEISUKE GOES ALL OUT
ON THE DOWNHILL
WE'RE FINALLY GOING TO SEE WHAT
HE'S CAPABLE OF
AND I'M WORRIED THAT
I MIGHT NOT MEASURE UP.
- I KNOW HE'S UP
THERE SOMEWHERE...
COME ON, OLD MAN...
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?
- IT DOESN'T TAKE A GENIUS TO
FIGURE OUT YOUR GAME.
YOU'RE WAITING FOR THE DOWNHILL,
AREN'T YOU?
BUT DON'T COUNT YOUR CHICKENS
JUST YET.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
ON THIS COURSE
WHO'S GOT A COUPLE TRICKS
UP HIS SLEEVE.
I GOTTA KEEP MY CONCENTRATION...
TRY NOT TO OVERTHINK THIS,
JUST KEEP YOURSELF TALKING.
- ( groans )
- DESPITE WHAT SOME OF YOU
MAY THINK,
SIX SECONDS ISN'T MUCH OF
A DIFFERENCE.
BUT STILL, THE FD BETTER CATCH
UP SOON.
IF HE ISN'T CAREFUL, THE GT-R
MIGHT WIN THIS THING
ON THE FIRST RUN...
NOT TO SAY, WINNING WOULD
BOTHER ME.
IT ALMOST SEEMS TOO EASY.
- OK, BUT WHAT IF THE FD
CATCHES UP?
IT'S JUST GONNA PUSH THE BATTLE
INTO A SECOND ROUND, RIGHT?
- IT'S NOT THAT CUT AND DRIED.
IF THE BATTLE HASN'T BEEN
DECIDED BY THE FIRST RUN...
HOSHINO WILL BE AT AN INCREDIBLE
DISADVANTAGE DURING THE SECOND.
I GUARANTEE IT.
THE FD WILL BE ABLE TO TAKE THE
LEAD SOMEWHERE.
- ( gasping )
- YOU FOLLOWING ME?
BOTH THE CHASER AND THE
CHASED KNOW
THESE ARE SOME
PRETTY HIGH STAKES
WE'RE PLAYING FOR HERE, BOYS.
THIS BATTLE IS IN A DEAD HEAT...
AND IN A RACE LIKE THIS EVERY
SECOND MAKES A DIFFERENCE
ON THIS COURSE.
( engines revving )
- OKAY... HERE IT COMES...
- DID YOU SEE THAT? HE USED THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE GUTTER
TO WHIP AROUND THE CORNER.
- THAT'S A PRETTY AGGRESSIVE
MOVE TO MAKE IN A GTR...
AND NOT TO MENTION DANGEROUS.
HE MUST BE TRYING TO KEEP
THE FD OUT OF SIGHT.
HOSHINO KNOWS HE'S GOT TO
DO EVERYTHING HE CAN
TO FINISH THIS BATTLE
ON THE FIRST RUN.
- ( tires screeching )
- HEAR THAT?
THAT'S GOT TO BE THE FD!
- WHOA, AM I SEEING THINGS
OR DID THE FD JUST PULL OFF
THE EXACT SAME MOVE?
- YOU'VE HEARD THAT OLD SAYING,
"GREAT MINDS THINK
ALIKE" HAVEN'T YOU.
THIS IS GETTING PRETTY TOUGH...
AND IT ISN'T GOING TO LET UP
ANY TIME SOON.
WHEN YOU'RE ALREADY PLAYING
CATCH UP THIS EARLY ON,
YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO WASTE TIME
OUT THERE.
I HATE WHEN I'M UNDER
THAT KIND OF PRESSURE...
GIVE ME AN OLD SCHOOL NOSE TO
TAIL BATTLE ANYDAY.
- OH HELL YES!
FOUND YOU.
FOUR SECONDS... IT MIGHT EVEN
BE LESS THAN THAT.
I KNOW I CLOSED THE GAP
FROM THE TURNAROUND.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY FOR THIS,
GOD FOOT...
I'M ABOUT TO DETHRONE YOUR ASS.
- MAN HE'S REALLY
POURIN' IT ON...
THE KID'S BETTER THAN I THOUGHT.
I MAY BE AN OLD MAN,
BUT I'M NO IDIOT...
IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOU CLOSED THAT GAP.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S
THAT KIND OF BATTLE.
LITTLE GIVE... LITTLE TAKE...
TOO BAD I'M NOT IN A
GIVING MOOD!
YEAH!
- NICE TRY, BUT YOU'RE
NOT LOSING ME AGAIN!
- HOSHINO MUST BE SWEATING MORE
THAN I AM RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- MAN... THIS IS
GETTING ROUGH...
I CAN'T HOLD OUT FOR TOO
MUCH LONGER.
THIS KID IS PRETTY GOOD...
EVEN IF HE IS FROM GUNMA!
DAMN! HE'S CATCHING UP...
RACING DOWNHILL IS NO EASY
FEAT AND HE ACTS LIKE
HE'S BEEN DOING IT FOR YEARS.
- YES...! I'M DEFINITELY
CLOSING THE GAP!
- MAN, I'M HAVING A BLAST
OUT HERE!
I CAN'T REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I FELT THIS GOOD.
BUT IT'S TIME TO WIN THIS THING!
- ( sighs )
- I REALLY HOPE THIS WORKS...
THERE'S JUST SO MANY
DIFFERENT WAYS
THIS COULD TOTALLY BLOW
UP IN OUR FACES.
I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK THERE'S
A REASON WE'VE NEVER TRIED
A STRATEGY LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- DON'T GET ME WRONG, FUMIHIRO.
I CAN TOTALLY SEE WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING AT.
BUT ADMIT IT, IF ANYBODY
COULD PULL OFF SOMETHING
THIS DANGEROUS, IT'D HAVE TO
BE KEISUKE? WOULDN'T IT?
- AT BEST, WE HAVE ONLY A 50/50
SHOT OF WINNING TONIGHT...
IF IT WORKS OUT LIKE
WE PLANNED.
YOU CAN COUNT ON HOSHINO
TO BE UNPREDICTABLE.
- WAY TOO MUCH ON THE
UNDER STEER...
IT'S GETTING HARDER TO KEEP
HER STEADY.
DRIVING A HEAVIER CAR HAS
FINALLY HAS COME BACK
TO BITE ME IN THE ASS!
I OUGHT TO KNOW BETTER
THAN TO OVERUSE THE FRONT
TIRES LIKE THAT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW BUT HE'S
ALMOST CAUGHT UP WITH ME.
I'M STILL IN THE LEAD.
I JUST WANT A LITTLE MORE
DISTANCE BETWEEN US.
SEE YOU LATER, PUNK!
- JUST ONE MORE...
ONE MORE CURVE...
NOW GET OUT THE WAY, GRANDPA!
- YEAH RIGHT...
I DON'T THINK SO!
- HEY GUYS, I THINK I HEAR
THEM COMING.
THEY'RE MAKING THE FINAL CORNER!
- ( all gasp )
- OH CRAP! HE'S TOO CLOSE!
- HOSHINO...
DAMN IT. I COULDN'T PULL
IT OFF.
- COOL... THANKS!
HEY, KEISUKE JUST STARTED
THE SECOND RUN.
- I... I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
I THOUGHT HE HAD A CRAZY LEAD...
HOW IN THE HELL DID HOSHINO NOT
DEMOLISH THAT FD?
- WHAT WENT WRONG, SIR?
- GENTLEMEN, THERE'S NO NEED
FOR YOU TO BE SO DRAMATIC...
HOSHINO'S OPPONENT DEFINITELY
ISN'T YOUR TYPICAL STREET RACER.
HE'S A WORTHY ADVERSARY...
AND HIS SKILL LEVEL CERTAINLY
SURPASSES OUR EXPECTATIONS.
NOW, I'M NOT ONE FOR DOLING
OUT COMPLIMENTS...
BUT I'M ACTUALLY IMPRESSED...
AND THAT'S SAYING SOMETHING.
- WAIT A SEC...
YOU'RE COMPLIMENTING THE JERK
WHO WANTS TO BEAT US ON
OUR OWN COURSE?
- YEAH. AND THIS GUY IS ALREADY
LEADING ON THIS RUN.
YOU SAID IT
YOURSELF, JOUSHIMA...
IF PROJECT D FORCES A
SECOND RUN,
THEY HAVE THE ADVANTAGE OVER US.
- I'M WELL AWARE OF WHAT
I SAID EARLIER...
BUT YOU HAVE TO ROLL
WITH THE PUNCHES, BOYS.
KOUZOU HOSHINO LIVES FOR
THESE MOMENTS...
THIS IS WHERE YOU'LL GET TO SEE
HIM REALLY SHINE.
- HERE WE GO!
STARTING THE SECOND RUN!
IN FIVE...!
FOUR...
THREE...
TWO...
ONE...
GO!
- THE FIRST RUN WENT EXACTLY
AS PLANNED.
NO TELLING HOW THE SECOND
WILL PLAY OUT...
THERE ARE A LOT OF VARIABLES
TO CONSIDER...
OUR OPPONENT IN PARTICULAR.
I KNOW ONE THING FOR CERTAIN...
THIS WON'T BE EASY.
- ( music Playing )
- I GET IT, YOU OLD FOSSIL...
YOU'VE GOT BETTER TRACTION
THAN ME.
- WHAT'S WRONG, ANKLE BITER?
IS THAT REALLY ALL YOU GOT?
I MEAN I KNOW ROTARIES ARE CRAP,
BUT THIS IS JUST WEAK!
- YOU CAN PRESSURE ME ALL YOU
WANT, BUT IT WON'T WORK!
I AM NOT LETTING YOU PASS ME.
I JUST HAVE TO KEEP HIM
BEHIND ME.
AT LEAST UNTIL THE TURNAROUND.
IF I CAN DO THAT, THIS RACE
IS MINE.
HE WON'T BEAT ME
ON THE DOWNHILL!
- THE SECOND RUN'S STARTED.
- SURE HAS.
- THAT WAS INSANE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A FD MOVE SO
FAST ON A DOWNHILL LIKE THAT.
LOOKS TO ME THE PURPLE SHADOW
IS OFFICIALLY SCREWED.
EACH TEAM HAS A LARGE CAR...
PASSING ON AN UPHILL IS DAMN
NEAR IMPOSSIBLE.
THEY PLAY THEIR CARDS RIGHT,
AND PROJECT D MIGHT ACTUALLY
HAVE A SHOT AT THIS.
THEY'VE REALLY THOUGHT
EVERYTHING THROUGH...
RYOSUKE'S A GENIUS.
- YEAH, MAYBE.
I DON'T KNOW...
SOMETHING JUST FEELS OFF.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
SOMETHING'S OFF?
I'M NOT SAYING RYOSUKE'S TACTIC
WASN'T BRILLIANT OR ANYTHING...
NOT AT ALL.
I JUST FIND IT HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT SOMEONE
LIKE KOUZOU HOSHINO,
A GUY WHO'S BEEN IN RACE AFTER
RACE FOR YEARS,
COULDN'T SEE THIS COMING.
AND ANOTHER THING...
HE CHOSE TO TAKE THE LEAD ON
THE FIRST GO.
I THINK HE COULD HAVE WON IF HE
PUSHED IT.
MAYBE I'M BEING CRAZY.
I DON'T KNOW...
BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME
THAT THIS IS ALL PART
OF A MUCH BIGGER PLAN...
GOD FOOT'S UP TO SOMETHING MAN,
I CAN FEEL IT.
- YEAH, YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
HE'S GOT TO BE WORKING
SOME KIND OF ANGLE.
I HEAR HOSHINO IS ALL
ABOUT STRATEGIZING.
IF THERE'S A WAY FOR HIM TO GET
BACK ON TOP, HE'LL FIND IT.
PASSING ON A HILL CLIMB
IS DIFFICULT,
BUT IT'S NOT UNACHIEVABLE...
GOD FOOT ISN'T DONE YET.
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
- HERE WE GO!
- NICE TRY...
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH POWER
THAT BOAT YOU'RE DRIVING HAS,
NO WAY YOU'RE GOING TO PASS
ME HERE.
- I SEE HOW YOU ARE.
WELL, TWO CAN PLAY
AT THAT GAME!
- ( crowd chattering anxiously )
- CRAP.
WHAT'S WITH THOSE GUYS?
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER,
I'D THINK THEY'D NEVER BEEN
TO A RACE BEFORE.
WAKE UP MORONS...
NO WAY KEISUKE CAN LOSE.
DRIVING ON MOUNTAIN PASSES SURE
AS HELL ISN'T A CAKE WALK.
AND I WOULD KNOW.
YOU'D HAVE TO BE OUT
OF YOUR GOURD
TO TRY TO PASS ON THIS COURSE.
IT SHOULDN'T BE TOO MUCH LONGER
BEFORE THEY HIT THE TURNAROUND.
AND ONCE THEY DO, OUR
FD WILL BE IN THE LEAD.
HE'LL BURN RIGHT THROUGH HERE
AND MURDER IT ON THE DOWNHILL.
THERE'S NO STOPPING HIM...
KEISUKE'S GONNA TO CRUSH THAT
FOOT GOD!
- THE TURNAROUND'S COMING UP...
WE'RE ALMOST TO THE TOP!
NO QUESTION NOW...
I'M GONNA WIN THIS THING!
- HEY, CHECK IT OUT GUYS!
THEY'RE COMING AROUND THE TURN!
- ALRIGHT!
- OH CRAP, THEY'RE COMING
IN SIDE BY SIDE.
- THE HELL IS HE DOING?!
- ( music playing )
- HOSHINO TOOK THE LEAD!
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT...
WHAT THE HELL...
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY
GET IN THE LEAD
BY PULLING A CRAZY STUNT
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
- MAN, THE GT-R DIDN'T HESITATE
FOR EVEN A SECOND.
HE KNEW EXACTLY WHAT HE
WAS DOING.
TOOK ONE HELL OF A RISK, BUT
IT SURE DID PAY OFF.
- IF KEISUKE HADN'T REACTED
IN THE NICK OF TIME,
WE'D ALL BE STANDING IN BURNING
WRECKAGE RIGHT NOW!
NO FAIR! THAT GUY'S
A DAMN CHEATER!
- THAT WASN'T CHANCE...
THEIR TURNS WERE ALMOST IN
PERFECT SYNC.
HE ONLY HAD ABOUT A TENTH OF A
SECOND TO MAKE HIS MOVE.
BUT HE KNEW KEISUKE WOULD HAVE
TO WIDEN HIS TURN...
WHICH GAVE HOSHINO THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO REGAIN THE LEAD.
- GAUGING TIMES WHEN YOU'RE
COMING OUT OF CORNERS
ISN'T EASY BY ANY MEANS...
BUT I THINK I'VE PROVED
IT'S WORTH IT.
- I DIDN'T SEE
THAT ONE COMING...
NOW I HAVE TO PASS HIM.
- I JUST GOT WORD THAT HOSHINO
OVER TOOK KEISUKE
AT THE TURNAROUND.
- ( sighs ) IT'S LIKE I THOUGHT.
GUYS LIKE HIM AREN'T GONNA GO
DOWN WITHOUT A FIGHT.
- WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSE TO
DO NOW...?
HOSHINO HAS GOT A DEFINITE
ADVANTAGE OVER US.
- I KNOW...
BUT WE'LL MAKE DO.
KEISUKE JUST HAS TO TRUST
HIS INSTINCTS.
WE'RE NOT QUITE OUT
OF THE WOODS YET,
BUT AS LONG AS HE MAINTAINS HIS
FOCUS AND KEEPS AN EYE OUT
FOR AN OPENING HE'S STILL
GOT A SHOT.
THERE ARE LIMITLESS
POSSIBILITIES HERE.
- COME ON, HOSHINO.
YOU'VE COME THIS FAR.
- WE CAN'T AFFORD TO MAKE
ANY MISTAKES .
JUST KEEP YOURSELF TALKING.
- DRIFTING, HUH?
FINE. WE'LL DO IT YOUR WAY.
- WHAT THE HELL?
- THEY SAID HOSHINO GOT
THE LEAD AT THE TURNAROUND!
- SWEET, DUDE...! DOESN'T
GET MUCH BETTER THAN THIS!
- YOU HEAR THAT...?
I TOLD YOU HOSHINO WAS UP
TO SOMETHING, DIDN'T I?
- THEY'RE COMING!
- IT'S A DRIFT ON DRIFT.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE!
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
EVERYBODY KNOWS GT-R'S
CAN'T DRIFT!
HOSHINO'S A FREAKING MAD MAN
TRYING SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
- I DON'T GET IT, WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON OUT THERE?
- MY GUESS IS... HOSHINO STARTED
DRIFTING TO SEE IF KEISUKE
HAD THE BALLS TO KEEP UP.
THE GTR'S TIRES ARE BOUND TO BE
LOSING THEIR GRIP BY NOW...
WHICH IS GONNA TO CAUSE SOME
PROBLEMS IN THE TIGHTER SPOTS
UNDER STEERING HAS
PROBABLY ALREADY BECOME
AN ISSUE ON CORNERS.
I BET HE THINKS DRIFTING IS THE
BEST WAY TO CONTROL IT.
SO IT DOESN'T TAKE TOO MUCH
TOLL ON THE FRONT END.
SOUNDS A LITTLE HARD
TO BELIEVE,
BUT IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT MAKES SENSE.
ON TOP OF THAT,
THIS ROAD IS PRETTY
NARROW, RIGHT?
IF HOSHINO WAS TO SWING OUT
THAT GT-R,
HE COULD BLOCK THE ENTIRE ROAD.
PASSING WOULD BE VIRTUALLY
IMPOSSIBLE WITH OVER STEERING.
NOBODY COULD GET THROUGH THAT,
FD OR OTHERWISE.
- I HADN'T INTENDED TO PULL OUT
THE FLASHY STUFF LIKE THIS...
BUT IF THAT'S HOW THE KID WANTS
TO PLAY, THEN I'M ALL FOR IT.
THESE PEOPLE CAME OUT HERE TO
SEE A RACE...
LET'S GIVE 'EM ONE!
SOMETHING THEY CAN TELL THEIR
GRANDKIDS ABOUT.
- THEY'RE SAY BOTH CARS HAVE
STARTED TO DRIFT.
JOUSHIMA, YOU HAVE ANY CLUE WHY
HE WOULD DO THAT?
- I DON'T GET IT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS COMMON SENSE
TO DO WHATEVER YOU COULD
TO SAVE YOUR TIRES...
BUT BOTH THE GT-R AND THE FD
ARE WEARING THE HELL OF THEM!
- WHEN IT COMES TO BEING
BEHIND THE WHEEL,
COMMON SENSE CAN SOMETIMES
TAKE A BACK SEAT TO LOGIC.
THE TWO OF THEM ARE
ALIKE IN THAT WAY.
WE HAVEN'T HAD A DULL
MOMENT SO FAR TONIGHT.
THIS JUST KEEPS GETTING
BETTER AND BETTER.
BOTH HAVE SOMETHING TO PROVE.
AND EITHER COULD WIN.
- THERE'S A
PERFECTLY LOGICAL REASON
WHY KOUZOU HOSHINO
BEGAN TO DRIFT.
KEISUKE, HOWEVER... SIMPLY FELT
THE NEED TO FOLLOW SUIT.
NOT SURPRISING...
HE LOVES TO BE STUBBORN.
HE'D RATHER GIVE INTO HIS
IMPULSE THAN TO THINK ABOUT THIS
FROM A LOGICAL
POINT OF VIEW.
COUNTERING A DRIFT WITH A DRIFT?
IF THERE'S ONE THING THAT
KOUZOU HOSHINO AND KEISUKE
HAVE IN COMMON,
IT'S THEIR ABILITY
TO BE STUBBORN TO
THE POINT OF IRRATIONALITY.
THAT'S HOW THIS WHOLE
THING STARTED.
AND I SINCERELY DOUBT THAT
EITHER ONE OF THEM IS WILLING
TO SWALLOW THEIR PRIDE
AND END THIS.
- DAMN IT, THE TIRES.
- I WOULD IMAGINE YOU'RE
FEELING PRETTY GOOD
ABOUT NOW, HOSHINO.
BUT THE GT-R CAN'T CONTINUE TO
DRIFT LIKE THIS.
YOU KNOW THAT AS WELL AS I DO.
FROM THE WEIGHT OF THE CAR TO
THE WEAR ON THE TIRES,
I DON'T THINK THIS RACE CAN GO
ON MUCH LONGER.
- IT SHOULDN'T BE
TOO LONG NOW...
KEISUKE'S GOT TO HAVE AN ACE UP
HIS SLEEVE.
BUT I'M GETTING AHEAD
OF MYSELF...
WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING FOR SURE.
- CRAP! IT'S VEERING TO
THE OUTSIDE ON ITS OWN!
- ( tires screeching )
- I KNEW HE COULD DO IT!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NOBODY IS SURE
WHERE IS THE END ♪
♪ NOBODY REASON ♪
♪ NO ONE CONFESS
THAT IT WAS WRONG ♪