- ( theme song playing )
- ( engine revving )
- FIVE. FOUR. THREE.
TWO. ONE. GO!
- ( boys cheering )
- WELL, TAKUMI'S OFF
TO A STRONG START,
WHICH ISN'T ALL
THAT SURPRISING.
FR'S ACCELERATE
MUCH FASTER THAN FF'S CAN.
- IT'S AMAZING WHAT A
BIG DIFFERENCE
THE WHEEL ALIGNMENT
CAN MAKE, HUH?
- WELL, SO FAR I GUESS
IT'S WHAT YOU'D EXPECT.
AM I RIGHT, CHIEF?
- I SUPPOSE SO, YEAH...
THE 8-6 SURE AS HELL
TOOK OFF LIKE A ROCKET
FROM THE STARTING LINE.
BUT I'M BETTING TOMOYUKI
DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
THE PEDAL TO THE METAL YET.
SPEED IS ONLY HALF THE BATTLE.
IT'S NOT WHO HAS
THE LEAD RIGHT NOW,
BUT HOW THESE TWO MANEUVER
THE NEXT FEW CORNERS
THAT'LL TELL US HOW THIS RACE
IS GONNA PLAY OUT.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
YEAH. COOL, I GOTCHA.
YOU'RE GONNA THINK I'M
YANKING YOUR CHAIN
WHEN I TELL YOU THIS, BOSS,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE PROJECT D
HAS GONE WITH THE 8-6.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE UP TO?
I MEAN THE FD WOULD'VE BEEN
ANYONE'S FIRST CHOICE
FOR A COURSE LIKE THIS.
- COME ON, ARE YOU
THAT ARROGANT, RYOSUKE,
OR HAVE YOU JUST
LOST YOUR MIND?
I WARNED YOU ABOUT THAT GUY.
BEATING HIM IS NOT GONNA BE
A WALK IN THE PARK.
- Ryosuke: I'LL ADMIT
TAKING THE LEAD SO EARLY ON
SEEMS AS GOOD
A WAY TO START AS ANY, BUT...
...IN A RACE LIKE THIS,
IT CAN WORK AGAINST US.
FROM THE STARTING LINE
TO THAT FIRST CORNER,
THE AMOUNT OF INFORMATION
WE'VE GIVEN OUR OPPONENT
ABOUT HOW THE 8-6
WILL HANDLE THE REST
OF THIS COURSE IS HUGE.
A SHREWD RACER CAN MEASURE-UP
A CAR'S LIMITS BY WATCHING IT
ACCELERATE FROM
A STOPPED POSITION.
JUST STEP BACK AND OBSERVE, AND
YOU'LL SEE THE 8-6 LAID BARE.
THERE WON'T BE MUCH TAKUMI CAN
DO TO COMPENSATE FOR IT.
THE MAXIMUM POWER OUTPUT OF IT'S
ENGINE WILL HAVE BEEN OBVIOUS.
HIS OPPONENT WILL BE
ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW THE OUTPUT
SCALES AS IT REVS,
EVEN THE GEAR RATIO.
WHAT IT BOILS DOWN TO IS THIS,
THERE'S NO WAY FOR US
TO BEAT A PROFESSIONAL
STRATEGICALLY.
- BUT IF WE AREN'T ABLE TO BEAT
HIM STRATEGICALLY, HOW CAN WE?
TECHNIQUE?
- TAKUMI IS GOOD, BUT I'M AFRAID
HIS TECHNIQUE WON'T HOLD UP
AGAINST A
PROFESSIONAL'S EITHER.
AND IT'S NOT AS THOUGH THE CAR
HAS ANY SPECIAL ADVANTAGE
IN AND OF ITSELF.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
OUR OPPONENT'S EK-9 IS FLAWLESS.
IN TERMS OF SHEER POWER
IT EQUALS THE 8-6.
MAYBE EVEN SAYING THAT MUCH
IS BEING OPTIMISTIC.
- I'M NOT SURE I UNDERSTAND YOU.
I MEAN... ARE YOU TELLING US
THAT YOU ACCEPTED THIS CHALLENGE
KNOWING THAT WE WERE
DESTINED TO LOSE?
THAT'S INSANE!
- DON'T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS,
FUMIHIRO.
THAT ISN'T WHAT I'M TELLING YOU.
THERE IS ONE THING.
ONE THING OUR FUJIWARA HAS
THAT EVEN A PROFESSIONAL
RACER DOESN'T...
CALL IT AN "X-FACTOR"
IF YOU LIKE.
IT'S THE REASON
I CHOSE HIM OVER KEISUKE.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS A RACE
WE'RE DESTINED TO LOSE.
WE WILL ALWAYS HAVE A CHANCE.
PROJECT D DOESN'T
EVER BACK DOWN,
NO MATTER WHO THE OPPONENT IS.
WE'RE FIGHTING FOR
OUR STREET CRED HERE.
- WELL, GENERALLY SPEAKING, THIS
COURSE CAN KIND OF BE DIVIDED UP
INTO FOUR MAIN,
DISTINCT SECTIONS.
RIGHT WHEN YOU BEGIN, THE ROAD
IS NARROW AND GOES ON LIKE THAT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
THE BEST PLACE TO MAKE A MOVE IS
IN THE SECTION JUST AFTER THAT,
WHERE THE ROAD GETS WIDER.
PROVIDED YOU'VE GOT THE SAME
SKILLS THAT TOMOYUKI HAS,
WITH ENOUGH SPACE YOU
CAN PRETTY MUCH ATTACK
FROM ANY ANGLE YOU WANT.
FROM THE SECOND SECTION ON,
BECAUSE THE ROAD
IS SO MUCH WIDER,
YOU'VE GOT A LOT MORE
FREEDOM WHEN IT COMES
TO CHOOSING YOUR LINE.
AND BECAUSE THIS RACE
REQUIRES GOING TO THE END
AND COMING BACK,
IT'LL BE INTERESTING TO SEE HOW
MUCH DISTANCE THERE IS
BETWEEN THEM
BY THE TIME THEY RETURN TO THE
FIRST SECTION OF THE COURSE.
- ALRIGHT. WE'RE COMING UP
ON WHERE THE ROAD WIDENS
AND VISIBILITY IMPROVES.
YOU CAN TELL THEY JUST FINISHED
CONSTRUCTION ON THIS PART.
IT LOOKS PRETTY,
BUT THE SURFACE IS CRAP.
AND THE SEAMS ON THE ASPHALT
ARE ROUGH ENOUGH
THAT THE CAR'LL JUMP AROUND
ALL OVER THE PLACE
IF I'M NOT CAREFUL.
GOOD ENGINE YOU GOT THERE.
BUT THAT SUSPENSION SYSTEM'S
GOTTA BE AS OLD AS YOU ARE.
NO WAY YOU'RE GONNA BE ABLE
TO KEEP IT FLOORED LIKE
THIS MUCH LONGER.
DAMN. SO EVEN ON
A ROAD LIKE THIS YOU'RE ABLE
TO KEEP THAT THING
UNDER CONTROL, AREN'T YA?
YOU'RE GOOD, AND THAT CAR
IS WELL-TUNED FOR AN 8-6.
BUT YOU CAN'T HIDE THE FACT
YOU'RE STRUGGLING.
I DON'T GET IT. WHAT'S THE
POINT IN A RACE LIKE THIS?
I MEAN HANDING THIS PUNK HIS ASS
IS FUN ON PRINCIPLE AND ALL...
BUT WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO LEARN
FROM THIS?
- HEY. KEISUKE.
- YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHATEVER.
- THEY'RE ON
THE SECOND SECTION NOW.
- I UNDERSTAND. THANKS.
WELCOME BACK. WHERE WERE YOU?
- SULKING IN THE FD, BUT
SINCE I LOOKED LIKE AN IDIOT
I DECIDED TO COME OUT.
- IF YOU'RE READY TO KNOW WHY,
I'LL TELL YOU.
- WE'VE PASSED
THE HIGH-POINT CORNER.
THE NEXT PART IS ALL
STEEP DOWNHILL INCLINES.
AND NOW THE QUESTION BECOMES
HOW MUCH LONGER I PLAY ALONG.
NOT TOO MUCH LONGER.
AFTER ALL, I'VE GOT A LITTLE
SOMETHING CALLED
PROFESSIONAL PRIDE
TO THINK ABOUT.
THIS IS FRIGGIN' RIDICULOUS.
I'M BASICALLY JUST
WASTING TIME NOW.
HELL, I KNEW BEFORE I STARTED
THIS THERE'D BE NOTHING
FOR ME TO GAIN BY
RACING AN AMATEUR.
GIVING THIS GUY
A LESSON IN HUMILITY
IS GONNA BE SO EASY IT'S SAD.
BECAUSE ONCE I GET AHEAD
OF HIM, IT'S ALL OVER.
- UNLESS I TRY TO SORT THIS
CRAP OUT IN MY OWN HEAD FIRST,
I'M NEVER GONNA MAKE
ANY PROGRESS. I KNOW THAT.
SO I JUST HUNG BACK
IN THE FD FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I NEEDED TO WORK OUT FOR MYSELF
WHAT YOUR REASONS WERE
FOR NOT CHOOSING ME.
AND I THINK I GET IT NOW.
KNOWING WE WERE UP
AGAINST A REAL PROFESSIONAL,
I'VE BEEN WAY TOO ANXIOUS
ABOUT TAKING THIS GUY ON.
I CONVINCED MYSELF I
WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD WIN THIS RACE.
BASICALLY ALL THAT PRESSURE
WAS REALLY STARTING GET TO ME.
IF I WAS ACTUALLY RACING HIM
OUT THERE NOW, I'D BE SCREWED.
SO TAKUMI WAS
THE OBVIOUS CHOICE.
- THAT IS PART OF IT, YEAH.
BUT THERE WAS A LITTLE MORE
TO IT ACTUALLY.
- TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
HOW FAST YOU ARE DEPENDS ON HOW
EXPERIENCED YOU ARE.
A PROFESSIONAL RACER
IS UNDER CONSTANT,
AND I MEAN CONSTANT PRESSURE TO
TIGHTEN UP HIS LAP TIMES.
STREET RACING'S A WHOLE
OTHER BALL OF WAX.
COMPARED TO THE
PROFESSIONAL CIRCUIT,
YOU GUYS ARE ON AN
ENDLESS VACATION.
TOMOYUKI IS DEALING
WITH THINGS RIGHT NOW
YOU CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE.
- THE WHOLE POINT OF PROJECT D
IS TO HELP ME DEVELOP MY THEORY
ON BEING THE FASTEST DRIVER,
SO, LIKE ANY GOOD
SCIENTIFIC STUDY,
THERE'S A CONTROL GROUP
AND AN EXPERIMENTAL ONE.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
TWO DRIVERS.
- IF THERE IS SUCH A THING AS A
NATURAL APTITUDE FOR DRIVING,
AND I'M NOT SURE THERE IS, ALL
IT REALLY MEANS IS THAT SOMEONE
WHO'S GOT IT WILL IMPROVE
AT A FASTER PACE
THAN SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T.
IN THE END, TALENT CAN'T
HOLD A CANDLE
TO PRACTICE AND SELF-DISCIPLINE.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
HOW GOOD YOU ARE.
WHAT IT'S ABOUT IS HOW
YOU GOT AS GOOD AS YOU ARE.
- BECAUSE OF YOUR
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS,
ONE OF YOU BRINGS TO BEAR
A MORE ORTHODOX,
CIRCUIT-DERIVED APPROACH
TO RACING.
WHILE THE OTHER COMES
FROM THE STREET,
.A KIND OF "NOBLE SAVAGE,"
SO TO SPEAK.
SOMEONE WHO'S TECHNIQUE
REPRESENTS A HODGE-PODGE
OF DIFFERENT STYLES
AND WHOSE ONLY GOAL IS TO BE THE
FASTEST DRIVER ON THE STREET.
DO YOU GET WHAT
I MEAN, KEISUKE?
OUR OPPONENT TONIGHT
IS AN ORTHODOX RACER.
AND AN INCREDIBLE ONE
AT THAT.
SO, IT'S NOT A QUESTION OF
TAKUMI BEING ANY BETTER OR WORSE
THAN YOU ARE.
- IS THIS STARTING
TO SINK IN YET?
WINNING A RACE
IS A MATTER OF EXPERIENCE.
THAT'S THE REASON YOU TWO
LOST TO PROJECT D.
AND WHY TOMOYUKI
WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN TO HIM.
- IN THIS CASE, THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN WINNING AND LOSING
IS A QUESTION OF DRIVING STYLE.
- I GET IT NOW.
SO THEN YOU DID PUT
A LOT OF THOUGHT
INTO THIS DECISION AFTER ALL.
BUT WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST TELL
US THAT FROM THE BEGINNING?
I MEAN, WE COULD HAVE AVOIDED
ALL THIS CONFUSION, YOU KNOW?
- I AM SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BUT I THINK YOU'LL FIND
MOST OF THE CONFUSION
BELONGS TO OUR OPPONENTS.
LOOK OUT! HERE THEY COME.
STRAIGHT FOR THE FOUR
SNAKE HAIRPINS.
- ( tires screeching )
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME! HERE?
- HOLY CRAP. THE 8-6 JUST GOT
PASSED ON THE FIRST HAIRPIN!
- IT'S THE VANISHING LINE.
- VANISHING LINE?
- IF YOU CAN FIND IT, YOU'RE
PRETTY MUCH INVISIBLE
TO THE GUY IN FRONT OF YOU.
FROM WHERE WE'RE STANDING,
IT JUST LOOKS LIKE HE
TOOK THE INSIDE.
BUT WHAT HE DID WAS ACTUALLY
A VERY SKILLED MOVE.
IT'S USED IN CIRCUIT
RACES ALL THE TIME.
YOU ESSENTIALLY USE YOUR
OPPONENT'S BLIND SPOT
TO CUT ACROSS AND
SLIP INTO HIS LINE.
SOUNDS SIMPLE, BUT IT'S NOT.
I HEAR WHEN IT'S TIMED
JUST RIGHT,
EVEN A SEASONED PROFESSIONAL
CAN'T AVOID BEING DUSTED
BY SOMEONE WHO USES THAT MOVE.
THIS DUDE IS SOMETHING ELSE.
THE FOUR HAIRPINS ON THIS
COURSE ARE WIDE ENOUGH
THAT AN EXPERIENCED
DRIVER CAN CHOOSE
FROM SEVERAL DIFFERENT LINES
WHEN EXECUTING THE MOVE.
WHEN YOU GET DOWN DO IT, THIS
COURSE HAS A LOT OF FEATURES
IN COMMON WITH
A CIRCUIT TRACK,
MEANING SOMEONE LIKE TOMOYUKI IS
GONNA FEEL RIGHT AT HOME HERE.
- DAMN! THIS GUY IS FLYIN'!
- Masashi: ANYBODY HOME?
- BACK HERE, MASASHI.
SO, 'BOUT THAT CHAT
WE HAD EARLIER,
DO HAVE A SPECIFIC PREFERENCE
AS TO THE YEAR?
- AS LONG AS IT DOESN'T HAVE
WINGS OR SOME FLASHY PAINT JOB,
I REALLY COULDN'T CARE
LESS ABOUT THE YEAR.
- YEAH, YOU SAY THAT NOW.
ANYWAY I GOT THIS FELLA
I DO BUSINESS WITH TOLD ME
HE'D LET ME KNOW
IF HE FOUND ONE, SO...
MM. YOU'LL SEE FOR YOURSELF ONCE
YOU'VE DRIVEN ONE, THOUGH...
A FOUR WHEEL DRIVE
DOESN'T REALLY SUIT YOU.
- WE'LL REACH THE MAXIMUM
SPEED FOR THIS COURSE
RIGHT BEFORE THE
BRIDGE COMING UP.
THE SECTION AFTER IT
IS A STEEP UPHILL CLIMB,
SO I'D BETTER PULL AWAY NOW.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO FINISH THIS.
HE WASN'T HALF BAD
FOR AN AMATEUR.
- ONCE WE'VE CROSSED THE BRIDGE,
WE'LL REACH THE UPHILL PART.
IF THIS BABY CAN'T PICK UP
THE PACE, I'M DONE FOR.
COME ON, 8-6!
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT!
- WHAT THE HELL?
LITTLE BASTARD'S ACTUALLY
KEEPING UP WITH ME.
I'LL BE DAMNED.
WE WERE EXPECTING
TO RACE THE FD,
SO WE SET UP THE GEARS
TO PERFORM BEST
ON A HIGH-SPEED
STRAIGHTAWAY,
WHERE THE FD WOULD'VE
HAD THE MOST LEVERAGE.
LOOKS LIKE THAT OVERSIGHT
IS CATCHING UP WITH ME.
MY SHIFTS AREN'T SYNCING UP
WORTH A DAMN ON THESE LOW-SPEED,
UPHILL CORNERS.
IF MY OPPONENT HAD BEEN A TURBO,
THIS WOULDN'T BE AN ISSUE.
DID THEY PULL THE 8-6
OUT OF THEIR ASS OR WHAT?
THE BRAINS BEHIND THIS OUTFIT
MUST REALLY KNOW
WHAT HE'S DOING.
IT WASN'T ALL THAT APPARENT
ON THE DOWNHILL,
BUT ON THE UPHILL THE FACT
IS STARING ME IN THE FACE.
THE 8-6 HAS BETTER SHIFTING
POINTS FOR ITS GEARS,
PURE AND SIMPLE.
ON THE CORNERS I HAVE TO
TAKE IN SECOND GEAR,
HE'S STILL IN FIRST.
SOMETHING ELSE I'VE NOTICED,
THE 8-6'S GAME HAS
DEFINITELY STEPPED UP
SINCE I PASSED IT BACK
THERE ON THE HAIRPIN.
MY OPPONENT IS MORE
FOCUSED NOW.
WAY TO KEEP UP WITH ME, KID.
IT'S KINDA LIKE I'M SEEING
MYSELF IN THE REARVIEW MIRROR.
- AT THIS RATE, HE'LL NEVER GIVE
ME ENOUGH SPACE TO PASS HIM.
WHAT THE HELL AM I GONNA DO?
MY ONLY CHANCE IS TO DISAPPEAR.
I'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY TO GET
OUT OF HIS FIELD OF VISION
LIKE HE DID TO ME BEFORE.
I'VE GOT TO TRY!
NOW!
- HE'S GONE.
WHERE THE HELL DID HE GO?
THAT'S NOT THE SOUND
OF MY ENGINE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NICE ONE.
THAT'S YOUR LITTLE SPIN
ON THE VANISHING LINE TRICK
I PULLED EARLIER I TAKE IT.
FIRST TIME A CAR I'VE ALREADY
OVERTAKEN ON A MOUNTAIN PASS
HAS EVER GOT OUT
IN FRONT OF ME AGAIN.
I THINK I'M FINALLY
BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT THE CHIEF IS TRYING
TO SHOW ME WITH THIS RACE.
AND I AM THROUGH
HOLDING BACK!
- HERE THEY COME!
- IS THE 8-6 OUT IN THE LEAD?
- I'LL MAKE MY MOVE
ON THE FOURTH SNAKE HAIRPIN.
DON'T TAKE WHAT I'M
ABOUT TO DO PERSONALLY, KID.
ON THE CIRCUIT YOU DO WHAT
YOU GOTTA DO TO WIN.
♪ COME ON BABY
LIGHT MY FIRE ♪
♪ READY FOR THE SHOW ♪
♪ NOW I FEEL YOUR LOVE DESIRE ♪
- ( thuds )
- ( tires screeching )
- THERE, SEE?
I DIDN'T BUMP YOU HARD ENOUGH
TO MAKE YOU SPIN OUT,
-JUST ENOUGH TO THROW
YOUR RHYTHM OFF FOR A SECOND.
LIKE I SAID, NOTHING PERSONAL.
TACTICS LIKE THAT ARE A
PROFESSIONAL'S BREAD AND BUTTER.
- RYOSUKE. SORRY,
BUT I HAVE TO KNOW.
EXACTLY WHAT KIND OF ADVICE
DID YOU GIVE TAKUMI
WHEN YOU TOOK HIM AROUND
THE COURSE IN THE FC?
- I DIDN'T GIVE HIM ANY ADVICE.
- WHAT?
- I JUST SHOWED HIM THE COURSE.
I MEAN, WE DISCUSSED THE
STRATEGY I'D COME UP WITH
BY DRIVING IT MYSELF, SURE...
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY
WE DISCUSSED
HOW HIS INSTINCTS
DIFFER FROM MINE.
WHAT HE'D DO
ON A COURSE LIKE THIS.
- BUT YOU DID HAVE
A STRATEGY, RIGHT?
AND HE'S BASICALLY RUNNING
THE COURSE ACCORDING TO IT?
THAT'S WHY YOU CAME HERE SO
EARLY THE OTHER DAY, ISN'T IT?
TO THINK IT THROUGH
WITH HIM IN MIND.
- THE FINISH LINE ISN'T FAR OFF.
IF HE PULLS AWAY FROM ME NOW
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
I'M GONNA BE ABLE TO CATCH UP.
- OH C'MON, THAT AGAIN?
THAT TRICK'LL ONLY
WORK ONCE ON ME.
THE 8-6 IS RIGHT ON HIS TAIL.
DID YOU GUYS SEE THAT?
THE EIGHT-SIX IS DRIVING
WITH ITS HEADLIGHTS OFF!
- HUH? HE'S DRIVING
WITH HIS LIGHTS OFF?
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
- MAN, HE'S REALLY KEEPING UP
WITH ME.
I CAN'T SEE HIM IN MY MIRRORS,
BUT I KNOW HE'S THERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
HOW CAN THIS JOKER MANEUVER
THROUGH A MOUNTAIN PASS
IN TOTAL DARKNESS?
HE'S CRAZY!
DON'T LOOK AT HIS TAILLIGHTS.
LOOK AT THE ROAD
IN FRONT OF HIM.
ALL YOU NEED TO SEE
IS RIGHT THERE.
I'VE GOT TO BURN
THAT IMAGE INTO MY HEAD
AND FOCUS ON FOLLOWING
THE LINE RYOSUKE SHOWED ME.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I'LL WIN THIS THING.
- ANYONE WHO'LL GO THIS FAR
EARNS MY RESPECT.
YOU'RE ONE HELL
OF A DRIVER, KID,
BUT WE'RE IN THE FINAL
SECTION NOW.
AND THE ROAD IS TOO NARROW
FOR YOU TO PASS ME.
THIS RACE IS MINE!
- I HEAR THE 8-6 IS TAILING HIM
WITH ITS HEADLIGHTS OFF!
- OUTSTANDING.
I HAVEN'T TAUGHT HIM THAT MUCH.
TAKUMI CAME UP
WITH THAT ON HIS OWN.
EXACTLY THE KIND OF MAGIC
I WAS COUNTING ON.
YOUR ONE-OF-A-KIND
TALENT FOR ADAPTING
WHEN PUSHED TO THE EDGE.
- THE FINISH LINE IS UP AHEAD.
IT MAY HAVE BEEN MESSY,
BUT IT'S STILL A WIN.
I WON'T GIVE UP.
IF THERE'S AN OPENING,
I'M TAKING IT!
♪ Forever, together ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Forever love and fun ♪
♪ Until the morning sun ♪
♪ Forever ♪
- SO, UH, WHY DID YOU SWERVE
OUT OF YOUR LINE BACK THERE?
- HMM?
- YOU KNOW, RIGHT BEFORE
THAT LAST CORNER.
AH, BACK THERE YOU MEAN.
THAT WAS JUST GOOD
OLD FASHIONED BAD LUCK.
SOME ANIMAL CROSSED THE ROAD
AND STARTLED ME.
I INSTINCTIVELY DODGED.
HEY, THAT'S JUST THE WAY
IT GOES SOMETIMES, RIGHT?
OF COURSE, THE UPHILL PART
RIGHT BEFORE THE FINISH
LINE DIDN'T HELP.
- I SEE WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING, BUT...
- YEAH WELL.
I GUESS SOME GUYS
GET ALL THE LUCK, HUH?
- WELL, I...
- THE RACE IS YOURS, KID.
I DUNNO IF THERE'S ANY SUCH
THING AS A "GODDESS OF VICTORY,"
OR WHATEVER, BUT IF THERE IS,
IT'S PRETTY EASY TO SEE
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT YOU
THAT DEFINITELY STRIKES
THE OLD GIRL'S FANCY.
AND I LOST TONIGHT.
- I CAN'T THANK YOU
ENOUGH, TODO.
I THINK I FINALLY GET WHAT
YOU WERE TRYING TO TELL ME
WITH ALL OF THIS,
AND YOU'RE RIGHT.
- IS THAT SO?
- HOWEVER BIG OR IMPORTANT
I FEEL AS PART OF THE
PROFESSIONAL WORLD,
WHERE I CAME FROM SHOULD ALWAYS
BE A PLACE I CAN GO BACK TO.
WHEN I'M LOST OR I GET
CONFUSED, ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS FOLLOW MY ROOTS UNTIL
I GET BACK HOME.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW
REJUVENATED I FEEL RIGHT NOW.
- I KNOW.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )