[FINIS humming]
[FINIS] ♪ London Bridge
is broken down, ♪
♪ broken down, broken down. ♪
♪ London Bridge is broken
down, my fair lady. ♪
I'll be seeing you very soon.
Sister.
[wolves howling]
[LEONHARDT]
Hmm...
[SOLDIER A]
Captain Leonhardt.
We're ready to
storm the mansion.
Good work.
It's so quiet.
Are we absolutely sure this
is where the target is, sir?
[LEONHARDT]
Do not let your guard down
under any circumstances.
That is our credo as knights.
As swords in service
to the Queen.
Sir!
[LEONHARDT]
Remember...
...we're dealing
with a monster here.
[CARDIA]
I hear voices.
[CARDIA] They have awakened
me from my slumber.
Why? I did not wish my
sleep to be disturbed.
All I wanted was
to spend my life
in a warm, comfortable sleep.
[LEONHARDT]
This is it.
Wait. That's it? The monster?
[SOLDIER B chuckles]
I was worried what we might find
on the other side of that door.
This isn't a monster,
it's a girl.
No! You fool!
Please don't.
[SOLDIER B]
Heh.
Huh?
[gasps]
[groaning]
Sir! What is she?
Stay right there!
If you move, we'll shoot!
[LEONHARDT]
Stand down!
You would point a
fire arm at a lady?
And you call yourselves
soldiers of the British Army.
But she's dangerous, sir.
Seize her.
But do so respectfully.
[IMPEY humming]
[LUPIN growls]
Impey! Will you please shut up?
What's wrong with you?
I don't think you're taking
this seriously enough, okay?
Don't forget, we're about
to steal the treasure
of a lifetime.
[IMPEY sighs]
[IMPEY] How much longer are
we going to sit here like this?
Are you even sure those guys are
going to be passing by here?
Listen up, Impey.
Being an exceptional
thief means--
[IMPEY] --having the patience
to take all precautions
and wait for the right
moment to strike.
I've heard it all before.
Here. I'm all done.
Thanks. You sure this thing
is actually gonna work?
I'm the most genius engineer
in the history of engineering.
Trust me.
I don't trust you as far as
I can throw you, my friend.
Sorry.
[gasps]
Hm? What, is it them?
[LUPIN]
No. That's the British Army.
[IMPEY]
What?!
That is not what our intel said!
Do you really wanna pick a fight
with Queen Victoria right now?
I know you don't wanna hear
this, but we need to abort!
No. We're doing this.
Just stick with the plan.
We'll meet after at
the rendezvous point.
Hey.
What happened to all
that crap you spouted
about thieves needing
to be patient?
[LUPIN] There's more
to that saying, Impey.
"At times, you have
to be daring, too.
Otherwise, you'll never make
it as a professional thief."
Troops, halt! On your guard!
Stand at the ready!
[LUPIN]
Gentlemen! Congratulations!
I never thought I'd see the
day the British Royal Guard
would stoop to kidnapping.
Her Majesty, the Queen, must be
proud to have you as subjects!
[gasps]
How dare you insult
my men, you dog!
Who in the hell do
you think you are?!
[LUPIN]
My name is Arsène Lupin.
And, sir, you've
got me all wrong.
I'm no dog.
No. I'm a dashing,
gentlemen thief!
Oh, dear. How strange.
[LUPIN] My prize tonight
is the captured princess!
Behold as I steal away
the damsel in distress
from the wretched hands of
you poorly trained beasts!
Beasts?
Fire!
[LUPIN laughing]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[LEONHARDT]
Calm down, all of you!
Don't scatter, men!
Maintain your formation!
I can't give commands like this!
[thud]
[LEONHARDT]
Oh, no.
[LEONHARDT] This is...
This is no normal smoke.
[LUPIN] Impey, you idiot,
this is way too much.
You--
Miss. Please. Your hand.
Oh, yeah. Almost forgot.
I'm not supposed to
touch your skin, am I?
That's the entire reason behind
wearing those gloves, isn't it?
The poison?
How do you know about that?
Relax, all right. Just trust me.
[LUPIN] Allow me to
introduce myself once more.
My name is Arsène Lupin.
For reasons too complicated
to explain right now,
I've come to steal your heart.
[CARDIA]
My heart?
[LUPIN]
Yes. Precisely. Your heart.
I'm confused. Why me?
Ah, I guess the drug from the
smoke screen is kicking in.
[LUPIN]
Goodnight, Princess. Sleep well.
[ISAAC]
Cardia.
You must never leave this
mansion, do you understand?
Because... you are a monster.
[LUPIN, IMPEY gasp]
[IMPEY] Agh! There goes
the steam engine again!
[LUPIN]
Jeez, Impey.
Are you sure this hunk-a-junk
is gonna make it all the
way back to the mansion?
[LUPIN] Hey. What's with
the big doe eyes, Princess?
Ha. I get it.
You're shocked at how
good-looking I am, aren't you?
[CARDIA]
No.
[LUPIN]
Lacking a sense of humor, I see.
Oh! Cardia,
you're finally awake!
Well, it's a pleasure to meet
such a cute young lady!
I'm the ultra-gorgeous, genius
engineer and great inventor,
as well as the man who will
one day stand on the moon.
Impey Barbicane!
Impey. That's the name.
Fame's the game.
Uh. Hi.
Umm. How do you know
what my name is, sir?
Well, why wouldn't we?
We've been looking for
you for a long time.
As a matter of fact,
we know a lot about you.
You told me you were
looking for treasure,
but you didn't tell me she
was going to be this cute!
[LUPIN]
Impey.
Just shut up and fix this
clunker so we can go.
Oh, yeah. Sure thing.
All right, work with me, baby.
Let's see if we can cheer
you up, whaddaya say?
Good as new!
I'm sorry. She's a beauty,
but she's stubborn.
You know, if you're feeling
down in the dumps,
I can definitely perform
a little routine
love maintenance on you, too.
Hey. I'll tune you
right up. Free of charge.
[chuckles]
Or not.
Impey. Just get us
moving already.
At this rate, we'll never
make it back to the mansion.
[IMPEY]
Yeah, yeah.
[LUPIN]
Hm?
Oh. You've never seen it before.
That, Princess, is the
industrial city of London.
She's a beauty, isn't she?
London is the home of our
beloved Queen Victoria,
and the political and economic
center of not only England,
but the whole world.
[IMPEY] Ah, I'm guessing
you've never stepped foot
inside a real city before.
In that case, you and I should
take a little time to-- Hm?
No way! Those things
are floating around now?
That poor guy sure has it rough.
If Saint hadn't taken him in,
he'd probably be
behind bars right now.
That's true.
Is he a terrorist?
Oh, yeah. He's bad.
You can form your own
opinion of him soon enough.
We'll be there in no time.
[CARDIA]
"There"?
[LUPIN]
Yep. At our stronghold.
[IMPEY]
Come on, Cardia. This way!
Guess who's back!
We just got in!
[FRAN]
Welcome home, you two.
Excellent work.
[CARDIA gasps]
Here, Fran. Look.
[FRAN]
Wow.
That's not good at all.
Well, don't worry,
it won't last.
The British Government is
far too busy fighting wars
against other nations right now.
By the way, well done, sir,
your sleeping agent
worked like a charm.
[FRAN]
Oh. I'm glad it was useful.
Hey, Cardia.
Come and meet, Fran.
Don't be afraid, he's one of us.
Victor. Victor Frankenstein.
I'm glad you're here.
Uh. Thanks.
[IMPEY] There's one other guy
we work with. His name is Saint.
Yes, and Saint is, well,
our patron, you might call him.
Nice fellow. He let's us
use this mansion, actually.
Heh.
He'll show up sooner or later.
Lupin. Is it really her?
Yes, 100%.
She's Isaac Beckford's daughter,
there is no doubt.
Wait, does that mean
you know my father?
The famous Mr. Isaac Beckford.
There's hardly a soul in England
who doesn't know his name.
Yep. True.
London wouldn't be
nearly as prosperous
without the contributions
he's made to society.
[LUPIN] Your father is
an unparalleled genius.
Isaac made things that
should've been impossible
given the science
available to him,
and he did it all on his own.
As an example, the Horologium.
The what? What is that?
[LUPIN]
A device capable of creating
unprecedented amounts
of concentrated energy.
It's more commonly known as
the eternally beating heart.
Isaac used it on you.
Embedding the machine
inside your body.
The British Army
tried to kidnap you
because they want to use the
Horologium to their own ends.
British Army?
That's right.
They were using the Queen's
personal guard as pawns
in their little
abduction scheme.
You're kidding me.
[CARDIA]
I... I never knew.
I had no idea
what this thing was.
Truth is, I don't know why I
carry such a terrible poison
inside my body either.
You could say...
I don't know anything.
[IMPEY]
Cardia.
This is where
you'll be sleeping.
You look rather tired.
If you'd like to call it
a night, go right ahead.
Wait, awkward question,
but how do you sleep?
[CARDIA] Much like my clothes,
my bed at the mansion was built
so it wouldn't dissolve from
the effects of the poison.
In that case,
this bed won't work.
Unlike my skin, my hair
doesn't do damage.
I'll be all right if
I sleep on my back.
Okay, then.
I'll have to talk
to Fran and see
if he can do anything
about the rest.
Until then, well,
I guess just do your best.
Good night.
Lupin?
I just wanted to ask you when
I might be able to go home.
I told you.
I came to steal your heart,
which means--
[rustling]
[LUPIN]
Whoa, whoa!
Wh-What the heck do
you think you're doing?
[CARDIA] By "heart" you mean
the Horologium, don't you?
I don't understand. Why does
everyone want these jewels?
I don't know anything
about my father at all.
And I don't know
much about myself.
I can't remember.
I have no memories of
anything that happened
prior to two years ago.
Sir, please tell me.
Why did my father
put this thing in me?
Fine, I'll tell you,
just cover yourself up!
It's not lady-like!
Why not?
A lady is supposed to
conceal her bosom!
All right then.
Count yourself lucky
I'm a gentleman.
If I hadn't been, Heaven only
knows what would've happened.
I wish I could be more helpful,
but I've already told you
everything I know
about your father.
Truth is, I have no earthly idea
why he put that thing
inside your chest.
Although, I do know why people
wanna get their hands on it.
Those men last night?
They were soldiers, but the army
wasn't pulling the strings.
There's a group controlling
them from the shadows.
Bad men. They're
known as Twilight.
Twilight?
[LUPIN]
Correct.
They want to use the Horologium
to do something terrible.
A large-scale terrorist plot
that would overthrow
all of London.
For all we know,
that was Isaac's intention
from the very beginning.
[CARDIA]
Are you saying that my father
is planning a terrorist attack?
[LUPIN] I'm saying the
reason I captured you
was to stop Twilight
from succeeding.
Cardia, we can't let them
acquire the Horologium.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
I cannot let you go home.
[CARDIA] Wait, don't go.
I can't stay here.
Please. Let me go.
You must be tired.
For right now,
try to get some sleep.
[LUPIN]
I will see this through.
If I succeed, maybe that
can be my atonement?
I hope I'm right, Master.
[ISAAC] You are a monster.
You bring misfortune to others.
That is why you must live your
life in complete isolation.
Yes, Father.
Oh. Well, hello there.
Do you live here in
this mansion, too?
[gasps]
[CARDIA]
Your leg! Poor thing!
Huh?
Wait, she's gone?
Maybe she got lost
wandering around the mansion.
No, I looked!
She's gone with the wind!
Lupin, you're the one
who saw her last, right?
What was she acting like then?
That's a very good question.
She seemed confused.
And a bit scared.
Oh, you think?! Well of
course she was scared!
"You'll never escape!
Ga-ha-ha-ha."
You say anything like that?
I might've mentioned it,
but I certainly
wasn't that crude.
[IMPEY] Agh! I can't
believe you did that!
Ugh! Lupin. Gah.
Are you kidding me?
She must be really scared.
Suddenly being kidnapped,
and then confined...
Confined? Please!
The girl is free
to come and go--
[ALL gasp]
I think I might
know where she is.
She's probably on her way home.
If she's on her way home,
that is definitely bad!
Twilight, the British Army,
and God knows who else
is looking for her.
If they get a hold of her,
then we're dead meat!
You're right.
We have to find her fast!
[SISI whines]
[CARDIA]
Thank goodness.
It's cold out here.
We should get you back inside.
[snarling]
Please don't!
No!
Cardia!
Don't scare me like that, okay?
[CARDIA]
I tried.
I couldn't help.
It died... because of me.
My father was right all along.
I am a monster.
I only bring
misfortune to others.
That's why I must
live in isolation.
No, you're wrong.
[LUPIN]
There's not a soul on this earth
who deserves to live
their life like that.
Love yourself. You're
more than you think.
My angel!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Oh, Cardia! We were
so worried about you!
[LUPIN]
Please stay with us, Cardia.
It looks like Sisi here has
taken a liking to you as well.
[IMPEY]
I've got an idea!
Let's throw Cardia
a big welcome party!
[FRAN]
Right now?
I think we should
probably go to bed.
[IMPEY]
Whatever, we can sleep...
They make a lot of noise,
but honestly, they're some of
the best friends I could have.
Your... friends?
Lupin?
Thank you.
You've all been so nice to me,
but I still don't know
if I should stay.
Sorry.
Although... this place
does seem really warm!
Then I think you ought to stay.
If that's what you want,
that's what you should do.
The problem is,
I don't know what I want.
You do. You wanna
know the truth.
The truth about your father.
The truth about you.
You said so yourself.
All you have to do is act.
No more waiting.
We'll go looking for
the answers together.
I'm Arsène Lupin,
the Gentleman Thief.
If there's something
I want, I take it.
If you stay here with us,
we'll help you find the
answers you're looking for.
Glad you're here, Cardia.
Don't freeze up on me.
It's unbecoming.
[LUPIN]
Let's see now.
I told you I was going to steal
that precious heart, remember?
But there's something
I didn't say.
In return, I promise
to grant you one wish.
A wish?
Yes, indeed.
You heard me correctly, Cardia.
This humble thief swears
to do everything he can
to grant your wish and will not
stop until the task is done.
[CARDIA]
No.
This might sound strange,
but nothing comes to mind.
I've never even thought
about that. Sorry.
Is that right?
Well, no rush.
The offer still stands.
Come on. Let's go.
[CARDIA]
My heart responds to his words,
and the sound of his voice.
Something I thought was tightly
sealed deep within my chest
seems to be rattling
as it stirs.
[chuckles]
[CARDIA] There are many
things I want to know.
Where is my father?
And... what am I?
Will I ever know the truth?