[gasps]
[FINIS sighs]
[FINIS] Why don't you stop
pretending to be human?
[FINIS] You don't have
any right to dream.
You don't even have
the right to laugh.
You're all alone in
this world, dear Sister.
[door opens]
She's getting some rest.
How do you think
she's holding up, Fran?
[VAN]
Dumb question.
After facing the reality
of what she truly is,
she's probably very confused.
Not to mention terrified.
There's a possibility that was
the objective the entire time.
Just think about it
for a moment.
All of Isaac's
documents were stolen.
Now who would do that?
It has to be Finis, right?
Yes, of course.
He must've known Cardia
was going to find her way
to Isaac's lab eventually.
What is this,
some kind of a game?
Does he just wanna
hurt Cardia?
I knew all along.
Not about Finis' plan.
But I always suspected
Cardia was a homunculus.
A life form created by man.
The Horologium inside
of her chest.
The ability to withstand poison.
The fact that she's Isaac
Beckford's daughter.
Taking all those facts together,
it wasn't difficult
to form my hypothesis.
Why didn't you say something?
[FRAN]
I couldn't.
She's so pure and
kind. Innocent.
She's just a normal girl.
[LUPIN]
It's not fair.
Cardia didn't deserve
to find out the truth
in such a horrific way.
She trusted him and he thanked
her by keeping her in the dark.
Better to know
the pain of a truth
than to live in the
cold comfort of a lie.
[IMPEY]
Lupin.
Cardia?
What's wrong?
This beast tried to run away.
No! Stop!
You're splattering mud
everywhere! Bad dog!
[CARDIA]
Drac.
Take care of Sisi, will you?
Make sure you walk him everyday.
[DELACROIX]
Huh?
Consider it done!
You should go back inside now.
You'll catch a cold out here.
[CARDIA]
Right.
I'm sorry.
[IMPEY]
Lupin!
[FRAN]
You can't go after her!
You don't even know
where she went!
What're you proposing I do then,
sit here and twiddle my thumbs?
[VAN]
Calm down.
Losing your composure
won't help her.
You're right, Van.
But we can't leave
her alone out there!
[DELACROIX]
What happened?
Is Cardia all right?
[YOUNG GIRL laughs]
[YOUNG GIRL]
I'm so excited, Mom!
[MOTHER]
So am I, love.
How about we sit down here?
'Kay!
Are you all right?
[CARDIA]
Stay back!
[HUNTER A]
Which way did it go?
[HUNTER B]
Damned monster! Where are you?
[HUNTER A]
Over here!
[ELAINE]
Come on!
Hurry!
[ELAINE]
Go on. Have a seat.
Here. It'll help
with the scratches.
If you're scared of me,
you can put it on yourself.
[CARDIA]
I'm not!
I'm scared of me.
[CARDIA crying]
[gasps]
[CARDIA]
This is what I have to do.
I have to find out
what I really am.
Is that--?
[sighs]
[CARDIA]
Huh?
[music playing]
[gasps]
[CARDIA]
Is that a keyhole?
[gasps]
Father's handwriting.
[crash]
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[VILLAGER B]
Get out here, monster!
[VILLAGER C]
We know you're in there!
[VILLAGER D]
Hand over the monster, Elaine!
We know you're hiding it
inside your cottage!
[VILLAGER E] You don't
want something terrible
to happen to Etty, do you?
There's no monster in here!
The girl's harmless.
She's no threat to you!
[PRIEST A]
Elaine.
You must listen to me.
She's a messenger
from the devil
come to wreak more despair
on the innocent
people of this town.
Just consider the facts.
We're suffering a drought.
Our people are starving.
Disease is running
rampant in the village.
Yes, I'm aware.
But that doesn't mean
the girl is to blame.
It's true: We are suffering.
But I will not let you
put that on a child!
Elaine.
Remove her by force.
Etty!
[screaming]
[VILLAGER G]
What happened?
[VILLAGER H]
What did I tell you?
That girl is a
monster from hell!
[CARDIA]
I'm so sorry. It's my fault.
Because of me, you've been--
[ELAINE]
Please, it's fine.
I'm worried about
Etty, of course,
but they're not all terrible
people in their hearts.
I'm sure they will treat
her with kindness.
[ELAINE coughing]
Elaine? Are you all right?
Of course I am.
It's me. It's my poison.
No, I--
Help us! Help us, please!
It's Elaine! She needs help!
[ELAINE coughing]
[CARDIA] Elaine. Don't worry,
I'll get us out of here.
[CARDIA gasps]
Monster.
This is all your fault.
You should've died
instead of my mom!
Amen, child.
Distinguishing God
from the Devil is hard.
But as long as there are
those who believe in Him,
the people will be saved.
Curse you, you unholy beast!
Taking Elaine's life
wasn't enough
so you've come back here to
unleash even more suffering?
No, I... I wanted--
Etty.
[PRIEST A] Calamity struck
our village again
because of the vile monster
you see here before you!
If we vanquish her,
we can bring God's blessings
back to the people
of this community!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
[CARDIA] Father, I know
I didn't obey your orders.
I'm so sorry, but I wanted
to stay with Elaine and Etty.
[ISAAC]
You can do no such thing.
And you know why, don't you?
[ISAAC]
Because you're a monster.
[PRIEST A] Men! Seize
that devil! Do it now!
Let God's vengeance
fall upon her!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[LUPIN]
You should all be ashamed.
Vile, disgusting people
like you don't deserve
to breathe the same air
as this lovely jewel of a girl
you see before you.
Though, I suppose I should
make proper introductions
before I whisk her away
into the dark of night.
My name is Arséne Lupin,
the Gentleman Thief!
You're here.
Yes, I am. Sorry it
took me so long.
Give us the girl!
If you protect that monster,
destruction will--
[LUPIN]
You're the monster here!
And you call yourself a priest.
How dare you deceive your flock.
Perhaps next time you people
should learn to
think for yourselves!
Instead of clinging to
the deceitful words
of a lying charlatan like him!
You snake!
You would hurt an
innocent child?
You would see her murdered
behind your lies?
[gasps]
[LUPIN]
Use your brains! Think!
If you can't even do that,
you people are done for!
Now I've told you the truth.
What happens next is up to you.
[PRIEST A] Why are you
standing there like that?
Go get that monster!
And bring me the thief as well!
Do not be led astray by
his insidious ideas!
Lest you allow these
disasters to destroy us!
Are you all right?
I hope you're not hurt.
I can't thank you
enough for saving me.
The others were
worried about you.
Impey, Fran, and Saint.
Hell, even Van.
Poor Drac's a nervous wreck.
[CARDIA] You mustn't involve
yourselves with me anymore.
The truth is, I am a monster.
Elaine trusted me.
And it cost her her life.
I think Etty was right.
I should've been the
one to die, not Elaine.
Yet here I am.
Someone like me doesn't
deserve happiness.
Take this, Lupin.
I'm not worthy of it.
Listen, Cardia. There's
something I want you to hear.
I've never told you my story,
or the reason I wanna
stop Isaac's plan
no matter what it takes.
It's because of something
my teacher said.
Your teacher?
Yes.
"In order to deliver justice,
one must steal from the wicked
and give the spoils
to those in need."
That's the brand of morality
he instilled in me, but...
I sensed that something
was eating away
at my teacher's soul.
You know why I became
a chivalrous thief, Lupin?
To atone for my sin.
Lupin, be faithful to your
convictions no matter what,
even if it means your death.
It's what I failed to do.
[LUPIN] At the time, I didn't
know what he was talking about.
I didn't know what
he meant by his sin.
[LUPIN]
But it destroyed him.
It was more than enough
to drive him mad.
After that, I decided
to set things right.
[whistle blowing]
[CRIMINAL A] Did you rat
us out to the police?
What? No way!
Someone betrayed us!
[gunshot]
I cannot believe that...
...someone would cry for me.
[LUPIN] After he died,
I learned the whole truth.
The truth about his "sin."
Turns out he knew about
Isaac's terrorist plot,
but instead of coming
forward, he ran away.
I had no idea.
I'm so sorry, Lupin.
Shortly after, I came
here to London.
I suppose you know how the
story plays out from there.
The past is the past.
But still, he was
a father to me.
I cared for him.
A man like that
doesn't deserve to die
over some stupid falling out.
Even now, I still believe that.
I have a past I can't
erase, just like you.
A past I'd rather forget.
Tell me, do you find
me revolting now?
[CARDIA]
Mh-mh.
I promise you this much.
I'll never abandon you,
no matter what happens.
We all feel that way.
It doesn't matter what you are.
It doesn't matter
what's in your past.
We're your family now.
Truth is, you're more
than family, you're--
Essential. You need
my Horologium.
You're right. I won't
deny that's true.
At first, the Horologium and
your connection to Isaac
were my primary motivations
for stealing you away.
But then, that night....
When I ran after you,
I did it because I couldn't
bear to leave you alone.
I felt this need to protect you.
[LUPIN] When I see you smile,
I know deep in my heart
I did the right thing.
You say you're a monster,
but I don't think
that's true at all.
To me, you're a normal girl.
[LUPIN]
Cardia. Are you ready?
Come on. Let's go home.
[CARDIA gasps]
Go a different way.
The villagers are waiting
just down this road.
But why?
I can never forgive you for
what happened to my mom,
but still, I don't think you're
evil like they say you are.
And neither did my mom.
She cared about you.
Cardia. You're not a monster.
[CARDIA] That idea has
been frozen in my heart
for a really long time,
but hearing her say that made
it thaw just a little bit.
I have destroyed many things.
And even though I didn't
do it on purpose,
I know that I can
never be forgiven.
I still believe that.
But even so...
[CARDIA]
I found this hidden in my room.
Is it from him?
[LUPIN] It looks like a
mathematical formula.
This is Fran's department.
It seems Isaac wrote you a note.
Shall I?
"Cardia, my beloved daughter.
If you ever get lost..."
[ISAAC] "...and feel you
don't know what to do,
go to London.
Visit St. Paul's Cathedral
where holy prayers
are offered up to God.
I'll be there,
beginning preparations
for my impious rebellion."
[ISAAC] "Too long have
you lived in doubt.
Too long have you
been in the dark.
The answers to all
your questions
wait for you underground.
Beneath St. Paul's Cathedral.
Come and walk towards
a new future with me.
All is for the sake
of this plan."
"I call it Code: Realize."
[CARDIA]
Lupin. I know that term.
I know it quite well.
It's very important to me.
What a coincidence.
[LUPIN]
I know it, too.
That term?
It's the code name for Isaac's
clandestine terrorist plot.
Cardia. That must
mean their base is...
...under St. Paul's Cathedral.
Is my father there, too?
[CARDIA gasps]
It's burning.
[FINIS]
Now,
let us finally begin the task
of creating of our new world.
I hope you're watching,
dear Father.
[laughing]