[IMPEY] You want me
to rebuild an airship?
I think I can probably
handle that.
[SAINT]
I'm glad to hear it.
The Black Gathering
is coming up soon.
I'd like you to enter
the race and win it.
Come on! You've gotta
be kidding me, right?
I've never heard
of that before.
Well, that's not surprising.
The Mafia puts it on.
It's a semi-annual airship race.
This year the grand prize
is of particular interest.
The winner gets the unpublished
writings of Isaac Beckford.
[gasps]
My father's writings?
You don't get the chance to see
writings like that very often.
If we win, we might find
some useful clues.
Indeed.
If we're lucky, those
documents will point us
in the direction of Isaac's lab.
Given that, I think it's
well worth our time.
I agree the papers are key.
But there's got to
be another way.
Heh.
Perhaps I can be of service.
[SAINT]
Perhaps.
You'll have to best
Herlock Sholmes.
From what I gather, he's
guarding the grand prize.
All right! We shall
enter the race!
You changed your
mind pretty fast.
[FRAN chuckles]
Lupin, I think there's something
you forgot to consider.
We don't have our own airship.
Have no fear, Fran, the
Gentleman Thief is on the case!
[chuckles]
Well, what do you say?
Can we count on you, Impey?
Wow! An air race!
I'll get to show off my
genius engineering skills!
[DELACROIX] That Lupin sure
is something, isn't he?
Where in the world did he
even manage to get that thing?
I don't know, but he said it was
"from a source that would
cause us no guilt."
Whatever that's
supposed to mean.
[LUPIN]
Oh, yes. That.
Don't worry, it's nothing.
[CARDIA]
Lupin.
Hm? Now where's Impey?
I don't see him anywhere.
[CARDIA]
He's in the workshop.
Apparently, he's
rebuilding the engine.
[LUPIN]
I see.
While we're getting the money
together, will you watch him?
The truth is, he
might need a hand.
[CARDIA]
Of course.
And if he tries anything,
you don't have to show
any mercy in punishing him.
No mercy.
Van recently taught me
an effective kick.
That looks quite
effective indeed.
There's that smile.
Makes me feel invincible.
I think you have a
really nice smile, too!
[CARDIA]
Thanks, Drac. You're sweet.
[LUPIN chuckles]
[IMPEY sighs]
[IMPEY] Make the walls thicker
to increase air pressure.
And then,
I might as well overhaul
the entire control system.
Impey. How's it going?
Hungry?
[IMPEY]
Hm?
Mm!
These sandwiches are great,
Cardia! They're delicious!
[CARDIA]
I'm glad.
I didn't do a very
good job making them.
[IMPEY]
No, they're amazing!
Oh, by the way, how's
the rebuild coming?
[sighs]
I've been trying a whole
slew of different things.
But sadly, there's still
not enough horsepower.
[chuckles]
Don't worry, Cardia,
I'll crack the code.
Remember, I'm the
genius inventor
who's gonna make it
to the moon one day!
[CARDIA]
You've said that before.
Do you mean the moon?
Yeah. That's the one!
It's always been my dream!
It all started with a
steam powered engine.
The first time I saw one?
I thought it was so thrilling!
Honestly, it was like my whole
world turned upside down!
I wanted to make
things like that, too!
Of course, it didn't work
out so well at first.
My master, or teacher, I guess,
told me something that
I'll never forget.
"Science is the power that
makes the impossible possible.
It's the dreams and
hopes of all people.
It can even take you
as far as the moon."
I was so excited.
I mean, it's the moon!
I figured, if I
could pull it off,
then anyone who saw me
would think it was amazing.
Just like I did as a kid!
And I've been trying ever since.
Trying to prove to
everyone that science
is the greatest hope we have.
Everybody makes fun
of me, of course.
They tell me that
it's ridiculous.
But who cares? I'll succeed.
So you see? A little rebuild
like this is nothing!
I am going to win that airship
race no matter what, Cardia!
Just you wait and see!
[LUPIN]
Ugh. Impey, you imbecile!
[VAN]
The damned fool.
I already knew he
was absent-minded,
but this is beyond
my expectations.
[IMPEY] In Asia, this is the
most sincere form of apology.
The kneeling bow.
Uh, I'm sorry, but the
rebuild's not done yet!
The race is going to
start any minute now.
Do you think he'll
make it in time?
[SAINT chuckles]
Who can say? Punctuality
isn't his strong suit.
Saint, honestly, aren't
you at all concerned?
Impey.
Um, we mustn't give
up on him yet.
He'll be here soon.
I know he will.
[IMPEY]
Sorry for the wait!
The star of the show
is here, everyone!
That rascal. He sure does know
how to make an entrance.
[IMPEY chuckles]
It's like the saying goes,
"better late than never."
Didn't I tell you
I'd make it in time?
Yeah, yeah. Come on,
we've got work to do.
If you'd shown up any later,
I would've shot
you full of lead.
Aw, c'mon, you guys.
You could at least try to
have a little sympathy.
My. What a fabulous vessel!
That's a tremendous ship
you have there, my friend!
Ah! Why, thank you!
You understand my ship?
[NEMO]
Of course! It's magnificent!
I'm a genius scientist
who will one day
expose the truth of this world!
What's my name? Nemo!
And now you know.
Oh, okay.
Look, to be completely
honest here,
I don't really get you at all.
But, hey!
Just take a look at the
functional beauty of my airship!
She's just like a young
maiden, isn't she?
[NEMO]
Yes, that's it! Brilliant!
Like a bashful young girl...
What's his name? Nemo?
[FRAN]
Yes, Nemo.
You know him?
Well, not really.
I suppose you could
call us acquaintances?
We met many years ago,
in the Royal Society.
He thinks I'm his rival.
I see. You're saying
he's a nuisance. Got it.
Wonderful!
Surely it was fate that led me
to meet a brilliant scientist
in a place such as this!
Now, my very perceptive friend,
I'll give you a tour of my
prototype airship, The Fulton !
I am in! Wait, prototype?
[NEMO]
Yes!
One day, I will perfect my
craft and build the perfect...
Perfect. He's leaving with him.
It's okay.
I can get her off the ground
if you need me to.
Has everyone finished
their final checks?
Observation deck is all clear.
[VAN]
Main deck, all clear.
The engine room is clear, too.
Look at you!
I would say you were born
to be an airship captain.
Welcome back.
Flight preparations
are complete, Impey.
We're all ready for take off.
[IMPEY]
All right, all right.
Look, I just got us
an aether transmitter.
So tell me, what did you
think of Nemo's ship?
[IMPEY]
Well, it was very impressive.
But, sadly for him, not
impressive enough to beat us.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Ladies and gentlemen!
The moment you've all been
waiting for is here at last!
Get ready
because the Black Gathering
race is about to begin!
Make sure that you win!
[IMPEY]
First we fly around the Thames.
Then we head to Big Ben.
Once we get there,
we turn and fly back.
If all goes as planned,
we'll be head of the pack!
We've got this.
Start us off at full
throttle, Fran!
We shoot straight up into the
sky until we reach altitude!
Roger that.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Three! Two! One!
And we're off!
[ANNOUNCER A]
The race has officially begun!
There's a vessel
taking an early lead!
It looks like a rookie ship!
The Impey, Princess,
and Manservant Express !
[LUPIN]
Hey! That's not funny, Impey!
I am no one's manservant!
[IMPEY] Oh, come on, Lupin,
what's the matter?
You can't take a little joke?
[SAINT]
I can't really say I'm surprised
by your choice of names.
[ANNOUNCER A] Ehh. That name
is far too long, so for brevity,
I'll just call it The Princess
and Manservant .
What? He left out
the important part!
[chuckles]
Uh!
Ship approaching! Eight
o'clock! Brace for impact!
[ANNOUNCER A] The Purple
Lightning Sky Pirate attacks!
High in the sky,
an intense battle has begun!
Quick, Fran! Increase
our engine speed now!
[FRAN]
Roger that!
[IMPEY]
Now we're talking!
[VAN] Impey, we can't
launch a counter-attack.
We have no guns!
Yeah, I know. I got rid of
them to reduce our weight.
Besides, to flee
is to win, right?
Right. As long as we can
stay ahead of the pack.
We've got trouble, Impey!
The paint's flaking off!
We're winning.
Why should we care
about the stupid paint?
[LUPIN]
Because this isn't our ship!
[MAFIOSO A] Wait a second, does
that look familiar to anyone?
It's our emblem.
That ship is ours!
Oh, my!
This is a shocking
development to be sure!
It's been discovered that
The Princess and Manservant
is not The Princess
and Manservant at all!
The ship was stolen from
the Adele and Brutus Firm!
Word has it there's a cash
reward of 20 million
for whoever shoots it
out of the sky!
Let me get this straight.
Does that mean Lupin stole
this airship from the Mob?
This is not good news.
Lupin, next time
you steal something,
please don't take it
from the Mafia.
[LUPIN] Well, the cat's
out of the bag now.
More importantly,
they're behind us!
[IMPEY]
Huh?
Behind us? Great!
We've got to get away
from those ships and fast!
[LUPIN] They're prepared
to self-destruct.
They're so blinded
by the reward money
they've abandoned
the race entirely!
[ANNOUNCER A] The Princess and
Manservant is coming under fire!
[IMPEY yells]
[IMPEY]
Status report!
Lower armor is hit.
It doesn't look good.
Air pump 12 is out
of commission.
I'm expelling the ballast water
to regulate our buoyancy.
[ANNOUNCER A]
She's evading the attack.
The Princess is tenacious.
I'll give her that!
She's maneuvering away
from the artillery barrage!
[VAN]
We're surrounded.
I hate to say it, but escape
looks impossible.
[gasps]
Impey, look out!
Something's coming!
Look. They're helping us.
That guy? I don't think so.
[NEMO] Impey Barbicane.
Your ship is truly fabulous!
However, I'm afraid I
cannot let you defeat me!
[NEMO] Impey Barbicane.
Your ship is truly fabulous!
However, I'm afraid I
cannot let you defeat me!
Behold, my ingenious
technical prowess!
No ship can match the
might of my vessel!
[laughing]
[NEMO]
No one can escape The Fulton !
Not even you, Barbicane!
Impey, look!
It's Big Ben!
Shake him off here!
Agh! Damn it!
Do it, Fran, crank the engine
up to the red zone right now!
Right, I'm on it! Here goes!
What?!
Yes!
[LUPIN]
Impey! Twelve o'clock!
You have got to be kidding me.
[CARDIA gasps]
What? Oh, come on!
They knew they couldn't
catch us on the first leg,
so they set up an ambush
for the return trip!
[ANNOUNCER A] The Princess
and Manservant ...
...is hiding up in the clouds!
Trying to avoid enemy fire!
[FRAN] Status update!
Engine 1 is fried!
Air pump's down.
If we lose one more
pump, we're finished!
What are we supposed to do now?
We have to figure
something out fast!
[chuckles]
I had an inkling
this might happen!
Impey, what is this?
[IMPEY]
Oh, it's nothing!
Just this ship's most
powerful secret weapon!
Here, Cardia.
Make preparations
for a counterattack.
Right away.
What's the plan? Tell us
what needs to be done.
All right, it says here
that first we need to
put Van in the capsule.
Wait a second,
what is it you just said
you're gonna do to me?
Hey! I didn't agree to this!
[SAINT]
Okay. We're all set.
[CARDIA]
Is this safe?
[VAN]
Hey!
All right!
And now it's time for...
Impey's Special Helsing Cannon!
[IMPEY]
Take aim! Prepare to fire!
Three! Two! One!
Blast them to smithereens!
But Van--
Right. Then we push.
[IMPEY] Van! Feel free to
shoot whatever you want!
[VAN]
Tch.
Impey, I'm gonna
make you regret this.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Wow! You'll never believe this!
One of The Princess
and Manservant 's crew
is taking over an
enemy ship on foot!
All by himself!
Impey, look! Nemo is back!
Roger that!
It appears The Fulton
has caught up
and resumed its vicious
attack on The Princess !
[NEMO]
You'll never get away from me!
[NEMO] The Fulton will
win no matter the odds!
[laughing]
[NEMO]
What the--?
[VAN] Anyone ever tell you
your laugh is excruciating?
Victory's ours. The Fulton
has been conquered.
Van!
[NEMO laughing]
[NEMO] It seems I have
lost this time around,
but I can promise you
that someday you and I
will once again face
each other in battle.
Until we meet again!
[ANNOUNCER A]
The Fulton has exploded!
[gasps]
It blew up? But where's Van?
[IMPEY] Relax, Fran.
He's on his way back now.
[screaming]
Van, are you all right?
[VAN groans]
Yes, I'm fine.
Go back up. Impey needs you.
[CARDIA]
Uh. Right.
Impey, I'm going to
make you pay for that.
[IMPEY]
I'm shaking in my boots!
You did really well down there.
Thanks, I'm--
[ANNOUNCER A]
Uh-oh!
The Princess and Manservant is
starting to fall from the sky!
This is not good.
It looks like it's
going to crash!
[DELACROIX gasps]
Well, Fran?
[FRAN]
Um, I have some bad news.
I'm afraid the engine is
completely overheated.
So, uh...
...we're going down.
[chuckles]
[IMPEY]
Uh...
Going down?
[ANNOUNCER A] Will they be able
to reach the finish line
before they crash?
They're in a ferocious
dead heat with death!
[IMPEY]
Hmph.
All right then!
If a crash landing
is what's in store,
we might as well do it in style!
Impey.
Trust me, Cardia,
we're going to win.
But the landing might
be a bit rough.
I'm not worried.
Impey always manages to
pull it off in the end.
That's true.
[SAINT chuckles]
A little bit of excitement
never hurt anyone.
[laughs]
[CARDIA]
I believe in you.
You'll succeed, I know it.
You can do anything.
Even make it to the moon.
[laughs]
Well, thank you for
the vote of confidence.
I think you're right.
I think this race is ours!
[CROWD shouting]
Come on, Impey! You just
gotta cross that line!
Let's go!
With Impey's genius
on your side,
you'll win the day
every single time!
You liar. We almost
died up there!
We won, but we destroyed
the airship. Should we run?
The thing is, we
weren't favored to win.
The bookies made
a killing today.
Fortunately for us,
they're happy about that.
They're letting us off easy
this time. We were lucky.
Do you realize how incredibly
reckless that was?
But even so,
this brings us one step
closer to your dream.
Congratulations.
My dream?
Yes.
First thing we'll do is get rid
of that poison inside of you.
Thank you, Impey.
[chuckles]
Are you having fun yet?
Yes, I am.
All right.
Let's take a picture
of our winning crew!
Squeeze in, please.
Come on, Drac, you and
Sisi should be in it, too.
Where should I stand?
[PHOTOGRAPHER A]
You, young man with the glasses!
Smile for me!
This isn't a funeral, son!
[LUPIN laughs]
He sure told you.
[CARDIA] When we're together,
I always have fun.
When we're together,
it makes me wanna dream.
No matter what happens from
now on, I know that this day...
All right. Here we go!
[ALL]
Everybody say cheese!
[CARDIA] ...this day
will be a precious memory
for as long as I live.
This is it? This is Issac
Beckford's laboratory?
[FINIS sighs]
[FINIS] Why don't you stop
pretending to be human?
[CARDIA]
What is this?
[LUPIN]
Homunculus?
[FINIS]
After all, my dear Sister,
you know exactly what you are.
[FINIS]
You are a monster.