[ISAAC sighs]
So beautiful. You look
exactly like my darling girl.
My perfect,
beloved little angel.
Cardia, my dear love.
You're my most precious.
[FINIS]
Why, Father?
Cardia.
[FINIS]
Why won't you love me, too?
Look at me. Please.
[gasps]
[footsteps]
Good, you're changed.
This outfit just
didn't suit you at all.
[FINIS] So what do you think
of my ship? I find it amusing.
[CARDIA]
Amusing?
You destroyed London
because you find it amusing?
Didn't you think about
all of the innocent people
who live in the city?
[FINIS]
What are you talking about?
It's not me but the Horologium
inside your chest
that will wreak
unimaginable devastation
upon this world, Sister.
[grunts]
Please, don't.
Stay away from me!
[screams]
[CARDIA]
It's hot.
At long last,
the awakening begins.
The awakening of
the Horologium.
Ah. Father.
[ISAAC]
Cardia.
My child. Hear me. The
moment is finally here.
The moment my greatest
wish comes true.
Father. It's you.
[ISAAC]
The world will change.
What "is" will no longer be.
You must guide the people
to a new paradigm.
Cardia, my dear,
everything begins with you.
[LEONHARDT]
What in the world is that thing?
This is beyond my
area of expertise.
Impey, any insight?
It's a killing machine.
We can try to put up a fight,
but The Nautilus
won't make it easy.
That ship is an impregnable
harbinger of death.
[FRAN]
Here's what we know for sure.
Based on the condition
of the victims,
it's clear what weapon The
Nautilus used: Zicterium.
[gasps]
Whenever Isaac took
over my research,
he probably stole some.
And took it with him
when he disappeared.
Makes sense.
From what I understand,
the so-called key to
initiating Code: Realize
was stolen, as well.
If that's true, it's
only a matter of time
before the enemy
breaks this silence.
Majesty. Tell us what to do.
I'm afraid we don't
have many options here.
Reinforce the army at once.
Recruit volunteers
until we have a force
capable of standing
up to The Nautilus .
Ma'am!
We don't have a clear picture
of what the other
side is capable of yet.
So, Captain, shoring up
our defenses is key.
The airship's armor
needs repairing.
How much time do you need?
It's hard to say precisely,
but a few days at least.
[FRAN]
That long?
What are you planning to do?
We've still got the Ornithopter
back at the mansion, don't we?
Don't be a damn fool.
That would be suicide.
Besides, you're in no
condition right now.
[LUPIN] I made a vow. I promised
I would steal her back.
Maybe I can't make the poison
go away, but so what?
As long as Cardia's safe
and back where she belongs,
then I can make her smile.
I can't touch her skin,
but at least she'll be alive!
Damn you!
Why didn't you kill him
like you said you would?
You had your chance
to take out Finis,
but you didn't pull the trigger!
The girl has a dream.
And I want it to come true.
The thing is, what Finis said
made my heart waver.
You're right.
Even if we don't
remove the poison,
she'll at least
get to live a life.
And with Finis gone,
she won't have to worry
about being used
for her father's
twisted fantasies.
No one will ever
come after her again.
But, Lupin, don't forget.
She told you her dream.
All she wants in this life
is to feel your skin on hers.
Cardia wants to be held.
Just like any normal girl.
Didn't you tell her you'd help
make that dream come true?
Will you quit now?
Will you give up on her dream?
You're right.
What am I thinking?
I didn't get to tell her, Van.
She doesn't know
how I really feel.
The truth is,
I'd give up everything
I have for her sake
and I wouldn't think
twice about it.
Even if it means
laying down my life.
I love her so much.
Then I have one job.
To make sure you have the
chance to tell her the truth.
We will save her life. Trust me.
Yes. You're damn right.
I'm not going to give up
until her dream comes true!
[IMPEY] How come I didn't get
an invitation to this party?
[LUPIN]
Impey? Fran?
I've a theory to share with you.
Do you remember what Finis
said back at St. Paul's?
He said if we destroy him,
Cardia is doomed.
Well, guess what.
If my theory is right, we can
save her and the world!
[footsteps]
Are the negotiations complete?
I certainly hope so.
[LUPIN]
You really think this will work?
[FRAN] If my hypothesis
is correct, absolutely.
[VAN] Either way, we need to
get Cardia out of there first.
Any idea where she'll be?
[IMPEY]
Hm.
I can't say for sure, but
I do have a general idea.
[VAN] A general idea?
That's not very reassuring.
An educated guess'll
have to suffice.
We'll find her.
I'm more worried about how we're
going to get close to the ship.
Impey?
I can handle that part.
But look,
if they hit us with a
concentrated attack,
there's not much I can do.
[DELACROIX]
Wait!
You're going to
want to hear this!
It's about Saint!
[SAINT] We sortie first thing
tomorrow morning.
Your Majesty,
please launch a full-scale
attack on the enemy's ship.
All right.
But let me make
sure I understand.
You're suggesting these
dubious-looking characters
are going to protect
us with their magic?
[SAINT chuckles]
Magic? Well, ma'am, that
is one way to put it, yes.
Trust me.
These "dubious-looking
characters," as you call them,
will be a great help
to you, Your Majesty.
What is that?
[FRAN]
I have no earthly idea.
[SAINT chuckles]
[SAINT]
Don't worry.
I promise you:
We will use it for good.
[GUINEVERE]
With all due respect,
was it wise to
accept those terms?
He defied this organization.
How can Idea support anyone
who would behave
with such insolence?
[OMNIBUS]
I have one priority:
To stop Isaac's nefarious
plot by any means necessary.
As the leader of Idea,
I see no alternative.
I see. You're saying
we need them right now.
All right. Men,
make preparations.
[IMPEY]
All finished!
I'm sorry about
the wait, everyone.
Saint. It's almost time.
[SAINT]
Indeed.
Just promise me you'll
come back in one piece.
Van, you're taking a British
Army airship, right?
Yes. I'll watch your backside.
If they even try to take you
down, I'll make them pay.
[SAINT] Well done.
You've thought of everything.
Van, you sure you
can handle that job?
I'd hate for you to
get wounded again!
You care to test me?
[IMPEY]
I'm good, thanks!
[chuckles]
Look.
I have come to see you off.
I've also decided it's
best I assist the humans
here on the ground.
All right.
One more thing!
Come back!
Do you hear me?
And don't come alone either!
Bring everyone back with you!
Deal.
[HERLOCK]
Are you certain about this?
If we shoot down Nautilus ,
London will suffer
even more damage.
The recovery process
will not be a quick one.
[VICTORIA]
Then so be it.
The people of this
country are my children.
Buildings may crumble
and bridges may fall,
but I will do what is required
to keep my family safe.
I must. As their Queen,
I have no other choice.
[SOLDIER A]
Your Majesty!
Preparations are complete.
We're ready, ma'am!
Initiate.
[LUPIN]
Don't worry, Cardia. I'm coming.
[ISAAC] At long last.
The moment is finally here.
You must guide the
people to a new world.
Cardia, my dear.
It all begins with you.
My father.
Finis?
[FINIS]
What are you trying to do?
You're such a fool.
In spite of everything,
you still want to believe
that you're a human being.
But you're not, Sister.
You're nothing but
a doll. Just like me.
[FINIS]
Everything that is, or was,
our brilliant Father, Isaac
Beckford, is contained here,
within my main body.
The puzzle is all
but assembled, Sister.
All I have to do now is put
the final piece in place.
That's me, isn't it?
I will act as a vessel
for your Horologium's
unparalleled energy,
and from our union,
an all-powerful
god will be born.
Then the world as we understand
it will come to an end.
[CARDIA] Then what?
What happens to the two of us?
[FINIS]
An excellent question.
My personality will
simply disappear.
As will the Horologium
inside your body.
[gasps]
You mean...
Yes. Your poison will
be eradicated at last.
How sad for you though.
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
The Horologium is also
your heart, dear Sister.
Whatever happens, you cannot
survive without the Horologium.
Your fate is to disappear
along with me.
[CARDIA] Is that really
what you want? To die?
Why not? I'm not afraid.
Don't you understand?
I was made to die.
If I fulfill my purpose, I'll
finally have father's praise.
He will love me.
[FINIS laughs]
I cannot wait!
Please, Finis.
I beg you. Don't do this!
You still don't understand.
[grunts]
[FINIS] The Horologium has
already begun to transform.
There's no stopping it now.
Your poison will grow
stronger and stronger still.
Until it begins to kill
everything around you,
even without touching you!
[chuckles]
This is why Father brought
you into the world.
So we could finish what
he started together!
See? You understand now.
You are truly alone, Sister.
Just like your little
brother, Finis.
[FINIS chuckles]
[NEMO laughing]
So you want to challenge me?
To face The Nautilus ?
Well, I do hope you're hungry.
'Cause science is for dinner!
Now, men.
It's time for Twilight to decide
the fate of the entire world.
Attack!
[gasps]
[LUPIN]
So that's what that does.
Looks like Saint's friends
really came through!
Whoa!
Now!
On it!
Let me.
Sir.
Oh, no!
[LUPIN]
Nice!
Do it, Impey!
Roger that! Hold on, everyone!
Fire!
Impey! Are we okay?
Not really, no.
But just remember that
we're doing this for Cardia.
What?
Look out! We're gonna crash!
Yes, we are!
Which'll put me inside
the ship where Carida is!
[FRAN]
Lupin?
Ha! You've changed your tune!
What happened to
"being cautious"
and "waiting for the
right moment to strike"
and all that?
Did you forget?
There's another part
to that saying, Impey.
"Sometimes a thief has
to be daring, too." Right?
[FINIS] What in the world
is Nemo doing up there?
Lupin.
[FINIS]
Sister?
[FINIS laughs]
Where exactly do you
think you're going?
[SAINT]
Drink this.
It will ensure yours
is a peaceful death.
[footsteps]
Cardia.
Lupin.
You're safe. Thank goodness.
Lupin. I'm sorry, I can't go.
[LUPIN]
What?
The Horologium's poison
has grown stronger.
I wanna come with you
more than you know,
but if I do, you could die.
Leave me here.
Goodbye.
[LUPIN]
Do you think I care?
To hell with the poison.
There's something you
need to understand.
I would give my
life to save yours.
Lupin.
I love you with all my heart.
I don't care if my
body erodes away,
I'm never going to
leave your side again.
Well, well. It's your
knight in shining armor.
[BOTH gasp]
I will not let you
stand in Father's way!
[screams]
Cardia!
Lupin.
Say, goodbye, Lupin.
Forever.
[gasps]