[ISAAC]
"Go to London.
Visit St. Paul's Cathedral
where holy prayers
are offered up to God.
Come and walk towards
a new future with me.
All is for the sake
of this plan."
"I call it Code: Realize."
[gasps]
[GUINEVERE]
It has begun.
If this plan is not
successfully thwarted,
then in order to
meet its correct fate,
this world will...
[FINIS] Now, let us
finally begin the task
of creating our new world.
I hope you're watching,
dear Father.
[laughing]
[FRAN]
Van! Saint!
She's nowhere to be found.
Damn it! Where could she be?
It's been three days
since she's disappeared!
Do you really think
she went to Wales?
If she did, maybe Lupin's
already found her.
Even if that's true, we don't
have any way of knowing
when they'll make
their way back here.
[IMPEY]
She's an angel.
My angel!
If someone's hurt her,
then there'll be hell to pay!
Impey.
[IMPEY]
She's the best thing in my life!
Don't you all feel the same way?
Of course we do! Don't we, Van?
We should split up and
keep searching for her.
I'll do another sweep
of the Upper City.
[FRAN] Impey, do you
still have the map?
[IMPEY]
Right here.
[bomb whistles]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[PEOPLE screaming]
Saint just ran that way!
[IMPEY]
Oh, no.
Trust me, he crossed
the bridge in time.
Come on. We need to get as
far away from here as we can.
Now stay alert!
I want a full report
on these explosions!
Ma'am.
London Bridge. The Strand.
King's Cross. They're all hit.
Reports are pouring in.
The full extent of the
damage is unknown.
Good God.
[SOLDIER B]
Your Majesty!
There is no question!
It's a coup d'état!
The rebels have occupied
St. Paul's Cathedral!
Die!
All traitors to the crown
will meet with the same fate.
Can we communicate
with Twilight?
They won't respond!
Finis. Damn you.
You traitor.
[OPERATIVE A]
Find the Queen!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[crying]
What kind of sick person
would dream this up?
Isaac Beckford, there's
no question about it.
His plan is finally underway.
Those men are with Twilight.
I'm sure of it.
Soldier, are you
running from a fight?
No.
[yelps]
[VAN] Tell me what's going
on in the Upper City!
It's a lost cause!
The rebels have us beat!
The palace is surrounded!
Queen Victoria's reign is over!
[SOLDIER G screams]
This is really bad.
[LUPIN]
It's worse than I ever imagined.
And the others?
They'll be just fine.
Believe me, it'll take more
than this to bring them down.
[gunshots]
Why are those soldiers
fighting each other?
I don't know what's going on.
But if Twilight's behind it,
you can bet things
will only get worse.
That's how things
always are with them.
We have got to
stop them, Lupin.
Yes, but we can't
do it on our own.
We'll need a little help.
The truth about Code: Realize,
the remedy for the
poison in your veins,
all the answers lie inside the
walls of St. Paul's Cathedral.
But that's also the enemy's
base of operations.
It won't be easy to get inside.
Which is why we need the Royal
Army to lend us a helping hand.
With the might of the
British forces on our side,
we'll have an
opportunity to strike.
And how are we going
to accomplish that?
What's the plan?
First, we're going
to save the Queen.
Trust me, if we rescue Victoria
from the clutches
of those monsters,
she'll give us
whatever help we need.
[LUPIN grunts]
I'm on a bit of a
schedule, friends.
Let's make this quick!
Lupin!
Is everyone all right?
It's Van!
Where in the world
did you come from?
Cardia!
You're here!
Impey! Fran!
Uh.
Listen, I--
Thank goodness. You're safe!
Cardia. We thought we'd
lost you for good!
[IMPEY]
It's true!
Oh! We need to find Saint
and tell him you're okay!
You guys. I never meant
for you to worry about me.
Sorry.
All that matters now
is that you're here!
You're back where you belong!
The truth is, we don't
know what to do
when you're not with us, Cardia.
He's right. Welcome back.
Thank you, guys.
As touching as I
find this reunion,
I'm afraid we have work to do.
Since you're here,
perhaps you can help us out.
We need to rescue
Queen Victoria.
We were just headed
to the royal palace
to accomplish that very thing.
We can't allow Victoria's
reign come to an end,
at least, not like this.
I'll admit, there are times
when I find her methods
hard to swallow,
but at the end of the day,
she loves the people of this
country more than anything else.
Well, all right.
Operation "Save the Queen"
is now underway!
[gasps]
[SAINT]
Tell me what happened!
[SAINT] I know you're there.
You can come out now, Guinevere.
[GUINEVERE]
It appears the monster
has returned to her companions.
[SAINT] Oh? Well, that's
certainly good news.
Good? Is it?
Isaac's perverted ambition
disturbs the fate
of all mankind.
We cannot allow this.
As the overseers of history,
our organization,
Idea, must act.
Take this gift.
Do what needs to be done.
[SAINT] Guinevere, she hasn't
fallen into Finis' hands yet.
Right now, Lupin and the others
are acting on their own judgment
to change fate and bring
about a different outcome.
We should wait.
We should give them
a chance to succeed.
It's not like you to
say ridiculous things.
Perhaps you've grown too
comfortable in your role.
You of all people know,
fate cannot be altered
once it's course is set.
Idea's purpose is
to guide the people
towards that inevitability.
Yes. At least, that's
what you believe.
[GUINEVERE] Have we
anything else to believe?
If your compassion
compels you not to act,
you know what will happen next.
Thousands of innocent
people will die.
Deep down, I know you understand
the error in that path.
[SAINT]
Yes. I do understand.
Or at least I thought I did.
But the more time
we spend together,
the more comfortable I feel.
And the more severe
my doubt grows.
What a truly unpleasant role
I've been asked to play
in all of this.
I wonder, will this
be your salvation?
Cardia.
[SOLDIER J]
Where is the Queen?
[SOLDIER K]
Find her!
Fortunately for us,
it appears that they
haven't found her yet.
Cardia, you're not short
of breath, are you?
No, I'm all right.
Well, that's good. Seems
your training has paid off.
[VICTORIA]
If you want me, here I am.
[SOLDIER L]
Your Majesty!
[VICTORIA]
I've grown tired of running.
So tired.
[VICTORIA]
Oh, dear!
That vase was quite expensive.
[CARDIA]
You sound just like her.
[LUPIN chuckles]
I know.
[static]
[SOLDIER N] Engaging the
rebels outside the library!
Requesting immediate back up!
This entire fiasco,
from the revolt to the
attack on the palace...
I have to admit, our
enemies are impressive.
Finis is going to pay
for all the innocent
lives we've lost today.
[LEONHARDT]
Stay strong, Your Majesty.
The best way to
punish these animals
is to make sure you
survive their attack!
Yes. You're right, Captain!
[BOTH gasp]
Stay back. Let me handle this!
[VICTORIA]
Leonhardt.
That was a close one, Old Timer.
Greetings, My Queen.
Have no fear,
the cavalry has arrived.
Arséne Lupin, the Gentleman
Thief, at your service.
I have ventured to the palace
to abscond with you.
[VICTORIA] Abscond with me?
I don't understand.
I'm afraid I don't have time
to explain in great detail.
Cardia, is the coast clear now?
Yes, but we need
to move quickly!
[LUPIN]
We're here for one reason.
To stop this rebellion
while there's still time.
We can get you out of here
in one piece, Your Majesty.
But I need you to trust me.
I have more than a few
questions, Mr. Lupin.
But for the time being, perhaps
it's best we make our escape.
[chuckles] I think
that's very wise.
The signal! Let's go!
Sorry about this!
Go on without me! I'll hold
them off as long as I can!
You ready?
Let's move!
[LEONHARDT]
What's this passage?
[LUPIN] It was used as
an escape route long ago.
It's no surprise you
don't know about it.
How the hell do you know then?
How? Because I'm
the Gentleman Thief.
Is it rusted shut?
No. But it's been
here a long time.
This might call for
a bit of gunpowder.
[LEONHARDT]
Gunpowder?
I'm not sure that's safe.
[CARDIA]
Wait.
[gasps]
Thought I'd save us some time.
Good thinking.
[VICTORIA chuckles]
[VICTORIA]
The infamous poison, I see.
Which means you must be
the one they call Cardia.
Your reputation
precedes you, my dear.
If we happen to make
it out of here alive,
I think you and I should
have a little chat.
How does that sound?
I'll keep it in mind.
[CARDIA]
It's so quiet out here.
[LUPIN] We're rather far
from the palace now.
Once we cross this bridge,
we should be safe.
[ALL gasp]
Did you really think
I'd let you get away?
I'm thrilled to
see you on the day
our plan is set in
motion, dear Sister.
Finis.
What is he doing here?
[chuckles]
You're not the only one
who's a world-class expert
at outsmarting
people, Mr. Lupin.
Sister, did you enjoy
the gift I gave you?
Tell me.
How did it feel to learn the
truth about what you really are?
You are indeed a monster, and
I don't mean that figuratively.
Not only does poison flow
through your entire body,
you're not even a human being.
[chuckles]
Were you surprised?
Please, tell me everything.
[laughs]
I'm not a monster.
Huh?
[CARDIA]
I'm not.
You are wrong!
I am not a monster!
[FINIS]
Ah! Your friends, of course.
They're the ones who put
this idea in your head.
I don't like them one bit.
I want you to tell me
everything about Code: Realize.
[FINIS laughs]
It would be my pleasure.
Code: Realize is the
gloriously perfect plan
our father concocted
many years ago.
It's goal is simple.
To reduce England and the rest
of the world to a pile of dust!
[VICTORIA gasps]
Are you out of your mind?!
I will not let you do this!
[FINIS laughs]
You're so brave! But you don't
know what you're saying!
Don't you understand?
You're going to help me make
father's dream a reality.
Let me tell you a little secret.
When you and I, the
Horologium and the vessel,
join together as one,
the world will
finally understand
the true immensity of
our father's plan.
We were created to be the
means to his masterful ends.
Father's Code: Realize stretches
further and goes deeper
than a mere coup d'état.
London is just the start.
The beginning of the end
for everyone in this world.
You saw it on your way here,
didn't you, Sister?
The destroyed cityscape.
Bodies strewn about everywhere.
We will watch with pleasure
as the world cowers in fear
in the face of its
inevitable destruction!
[FINIS laughs]
Oh, look at you!
Do you really think
covering your eyes and ears
will change anything?
[laughs]
Oh, relax.
Your will has no bearing
in these proceedings!
After all, your very existence
destroys every single thing
in its path, does it not?
[FINIS laughs]
Just leave her alone!
Don't you see?
You're the one who's going
to destroy the world, Sister.
It's your fate!
It's the sole purpose you
were designed to fulfill.
[chuckles]
Everyone is going to
die because of you.
Everyone! Even your friends!
I told you to leave her alone!
[FINIS]
You're too loud, Mr. Lupin.
[gunshot]
Lupin!
See? You're to blame
for his demise as well.
Take my sister away.
[IMPEY]
We're here!
Your knights in shining
armor have arrived!
We've come to save
the day, Cardia!
It's Impey.
Who else would it be?
--[thudding]
--[yelling]
Van!
Thank you. Let's
get out of here.
Majesty. Forgive me.
Jump! Hurry!
[FINIS]
Bring her back.
My sister has a very
important part to play.
Every last one of them will die.
And it's all because of her!
[CARDIA] Mountains of rubble
spilling all over the city.
Motionless bodies.
Pools of blood.
[CARDIA] Is it really
my fate to bring about
such fear and devastation?
If indeed that's true,
what does that make me?
[VICTORIA]
So we're clear,
you're saying this horrific
coup d'état was perpetrated
in service of fulfilling
Isaac Beckford's plan, yes?
Yes. That's why we're headed
to St Paul's Cathedral.
To meet Finis head on and
put a stop to him for good.
But we need your help.
Round up all of your men.
We'll use them to drive the
rebels out of St Paul's.
I've already lost so
many of my soldiers.
That said...
The British Army
will stand with you.
We've no choice.
If I let them seize
control of London,
it won't be long before
the entire Empire
crumbles beneath my feet.
Did we just form a united
front? Or am I mistaken?
A royal Queen and a gang of
thieves banding together as one?
[VICTORIA chuckles]
What strange times.
You have my word, Lupin.
I'll make sure Finis
pays for his crimes.
He'll rue the day he raised
his sword to the royal crown.
[SAINT]
Cardia.
[CARDIA]
Saint.
How did you know I was here?
Haven't you figured it
out yet? I know everything.
[chuckles]
What's wrong, Cardia?
You seem sad.
I can hardly blame you,
not after you've learned so
much in such a short time.
However, there's
nothing to fear.
In your journey to
uncover the truth,
take comfort in knowing
you won't be alone.
You have many friends
on whom you can depend.
Friends you can trust.
Friends who will be there for
you no matter the circumstances.
Saint?
[SAINT] I... I'm sure
I love you, Cardia, truly.
I'm sure I love the
others, as well.
I want to see the answer
you find for yourselves.
I want that more than anything.
"I'm sure."
I imagine to you that
phrase sounds rather silly.
I imagine it's hard
to comprehend.
Not even understanding
your own feelings.
[SAINT]
I am a disciple of Idea.
I have a destiny I must fulfill.
Idea?
Cardia, my dear,
I'm here for one reason.
I have come here to kill you.
[gasps]