[CARDIA] I want you to tell me
everything about Code: Realize.
Code: Realize is the
gloriously perfect plan
our father concocted
many years ago.
It's goal is simple.
To reduce England and the rest
of the world to a pile of dust!
[FINIS laughs]
Aww, look at you!
Covering your eyes and ears
won't change anything!
After all, your very
existence destroys
every single thing in
its path, does it not?
[FINIS laughing]
[SAINT]
I am a disciple of Idea.
I have a destiny I must fulfill.
Idea?
Cardia, my dear,
I'm here for one reason.
I have come here to kill you.
[gasps]
[SAINT] Since time immemorial,
there has existed in this world
a clandestine organization that
oversees all human history.
It's called Idea.
Throughout the course of time,
they use any means
necessary to remove errors
with the express purpose
of guiding mankind
toward the correct destiny.
The correct destiny?
[SAINT] Humans are weak.
As such, they make mistakes.
That's why Idea exists,
to set those mistakes right.
No matter the cost.
The reality is this:
They believe you're one
of those mistakes.
They want to eliminate you.
The cursed "Children of Isaac."
The keys to the activation
of Code: Realize.
The existence of you and your
siblings will disturb history
and invite disasters the likes
of which have not been seen.
I'm sorry, but this
can't be ignored.
So that's why you've
come here to kill me?
[SAINT]
Here.
Drink this. It will ensure
yours is a peaceful death.
Isaac's insidious plan must
be stopped at all costs.
[FINIS] You saw it on your way
here, didn't you, Sister?
The destroyed cityscape.
Bodies strewn about everywhere.
[FINIS chuckles]
[FINIS] Everyone is going
to die because of you.
Everyone! Even your friends!
Cardia, you mustn't.
[CARDIA]
I won't use it.
It just needs to look
like I took it from you.
It's all right.
I'll be okay.
Thank you for worrying
about me so much.
[VAN]
You two.
We're having a meeting.
On my way.
Saint.
[SAINT] I pray fortune
will be on your side.
Where's he off to?
Is everything all right?
Uh. Yes. We're fine.
Hi, Drac!
Well, there you are!
[SISI barks]
Hi, Sisi!
We're lucky. The army
escorted them here.
To be on the safe side,
I brought a few things I
thought might come in handy.
[IMPEY chuckles]
Aww! Good boy!
Take your hands off
of me right now!
[IMPEY] Don't get mad!
It's a compliment, Drac!
[DELACROIX]
I don't need a compliment
from the likes of you!
Where is Lupin?
Uh.
He's being treated in the
medical tent over there.
He's fine. He just
needs a little rest.
But don't worry, he'll be
back on his feet in no time.
[DELACROIX]
Huh? He was hurt?
He sure was! He's laid up
in a hospital bed right now!
Guess that'll teach him to brag
about being nimble all the time.
On the other hand, Lupin's been
on the move a lot lately.
A little "R and R" might
do him some good!
You're so compassionate, Impey.
I know!
Not to brag myself,
but a lotta people say
compassion is my middle name!
What's your last name
then, "talks-a-lot"?
That's mean!
Why do you always have
to go outta your way
to hurt my feelings, Drac?
[DELACROIX]
The truth hurts, doesn't it?
Are the men gathered?
Yes.
We have 10,000
able-bodied troops
ready to go to war
for their Queen.
Many are wounded,
but morale is high.
I promise you this much,
Your Majesty,
the men have not lost their
pride as British soldiers.
The bravery of these men
instills me with
immeasurable pride.
There's no doubt:
With them by my side,
Twilight will fall.
Stand at the ready,
men, because at dawn,
we march on St Paul's Cathedral.
Make preparations at once.
[SOLDIERS]
Right!
[groaning]
[DELACROIX]
Hm?
What's wrong?
[barks]
[LUPIN chuckles]
[DELACROIX]
Glad you're awake.
[LUPIN]
Huh? Oh. Drac. You're here.
Yeah.
Cardia was with me too,
till just a few moments ago.
She left in a hurry.
I'm not sure why.
[VAN]
Cardia?
You wanna tell me what
happened with the Count?
[VAN sighs]
Well, I'm not going
to force your hand.
You know, you've changed
since I first met you.
It means a lot that you
and I have become friends.
You've taught me so
many different things.
I would be nowhere without you.
Don't thank me just yet.
Believe me, this whole
thing is far from over.
For both of us.
Uh?
The next time I cross
paths with Finis,
I won't let him get away.
I'll put an end to him.
But once the job is done,
I'm afraid there is
a debt I have to pay.
I made a promise and
I can't take it back.
After I have my revenge,
my life is Delacroix's.
[CARDIA]
But, Van...
You're my friend and
I don't want you to go.
I have to.
Outside of my desire to
bring justice to Finis,
there are no chains
binding me to this life.
[IMPEY humming]
[IMPEY]
It's rough around the edges,
but it'll make some
pretty fireworks!
Just wait.
[FRAN]
Whoa!
[yelping]
Come on, take it easy, Fran.
You scared me half to death!
Huh? Oh. Sorry.
Look at this, Impey.
[IMPEY]
Hm?
This is that thing that
Cardia found, right?
What am I looking at, Fran?
There's a name here
that might ring a bell.
Do you remember Nemo?
Nemo? Nemo from
the airship race?
[FRAN]
Yes.
There's a page missing, so
I'm not sure about the details.
This much is clear.
It would appear Nemo was deeply
involved in Isaac's plan.
Are you kidding me?
I wish I was, Impey.
The name "Nautilus" is
written down here as well.
Though I'm not sure
what it means.
[IMPEY]
Nautlilus?
That sounds really
familiar to me.
Ah! Come on, Impey! Think!
Agh! If Saint were here,
he'd figure it out!
Yes, he would.
But he's not.
He'll come back, right?
Huh?
Well, Fran.
Lupin's hurt real bad.
We don't know where Saint is.
And London's in dire straights.
I'd be a liar if I said I wasn't
more than a little discouraged
right about now.
But I'll do anything to keep
Cardia outta harm's way,
even if it means laying
my life on the line!
Same for me.
I'm afraid, but there's no way
I'm going to give up hope.
We just have to
keep our heads up.
As long as we stay positive
and stick together,
I have no doubt it
will all be fine.
Trust me.
When this is all over,
Cardia will be happy again.
Should I be worried?
'Cause it sounds like
a new rival in love
is jumping in the ring.
[FRAN chuckles]
Well, maybe so.
[BOTH laugh]
You're a member of
our organization.
She's nothing more than
a mistake of history
that must be
properly dealt with.
Forget about her.
And if I can't?
What happens then?
[GUINEVERE]
As a fellow member of Idea,
I will have to open your eyes.
[SAINT]
Farewell.
[SOLDIER G]
Thanks.
Would you like some bread?
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
So, um, are you in pain?
I was.
But thankfully, the medicine
is starting to kick in.
My body feels a
bit heavy, is all.
Oh.
This is my treasure.
What a cute child.
I miss them both.
I can't wait to get back home.
So I can hold them in my arms.
[SOLDIER J chuckles]
[rustling]
[sighs]
I'm glad to see you're awake.
If you're well enough to give
your rations to a dog,
then get up and work.
You're a real sweetheart.
You know, when I look
at you I think, "Sympathy."
No one else comes
to see me in here,
so I have to settle for him.
Right? Good boy!
You fool. Everyone's working
extra hard to cover for you.
Stop wasting time. Get ready.
[LUPIN]
Hmph.
What's Cardia doing?
Truth is,
I'm worried she's anguishing
over that bile Finis spewed.
I just hope she's not off crying
somewhere all by herself.
It's driving me mad.
I wish I could help her somehow.
But look at me.
You're in love with her, right?
In love? No!
I thought you would be a
much better liar than that.
[LUPIN] I'm not lying,
Van! I promise you!
If that's really true, then
what are you so worked up about?
There's no guarantee you'll
both still be alive tomorrow.
Trust me, regret
is a foolish thing.
From a man who has
nothing left in this world,
tell her what you're feeling.
Your words might be the chain
that binds her to this life.
If you don't, she
could end up like me.
Van.
[LUPIN laughs]
You are the last
person I thought
would give me advice like that.
What gives, did
hell freeze over?
Sadly, our game of friendship
is about to come to an end.
Consider it a parting
gift of sorts.
[barks]
[CARDIA]
Uh.
[gasps]
[LUPIN]
Cardia.
Are you crying?
I'm scared.
I just realized that I'm scared.
Scared of dying,
and because I've never
known this feeling.
I'm so afraid.
I understand.
But I promise you, we will
always be by your side, Cardia.
No matter what happens,
I swear, we will protect you.
Trust me. There's
nothing to be afraid of.
[CARDIA] I don't know how
you stay strong like this.
Aren't you scared?
Yes. Of course.
Don't you get it?
I never wanted you to
get hurt for my sake!
I was happy you were willing
to shield me from harm,
and yet...
I can't stand the thought of you
hurting yourself to protect me.
If you died,
I don't think I'd be able
to forgive myself for it.
Not now. And not ever.
I don't want you to put yourself
at risk on my account,
not anymore.
Don't you see?
I don't want you to die for me.
You understand?
[LUPIN]
Cardia.
[CARDIA]
Lupin. It's strange...
But when I look at you,
my chest hurts.
It's more than I can bear.
Truly. It hurts me. But at
the same time, it feels good.
Sorry.
I'm not going to die, Cardia.
I'm going to live a long time.
And I will protect you
every step of the way.
Lupin.
[IMPEY]
Look at that.
It appears Princess Cardia's
Prince is a Gentleman Thief.
Well, of course she likes him.
I am his partner after all.
Right. Look how
happy she looks.
We have to stay alive.
[IMPEY]
Huh?
I would gladly put my life
on the line for her sake.
But still... I think she'd
prefer it if we survived.
[chuckles]
Right!
I'll ask one more time.
If we do this, we're all
risking our lives.
Are you guys with me or not?
Finis is still alive,
isn't he? Count me in.
I will not stop until
he's destroyed.
I'm not walking away from this.
We've come way too far.
I am the best engineer
who's ever lived.
Not to mention a
soldier for true love!
Oh!
Uh, sorry.
I think what I was
trying to say is this:
For you I'd do anything,
even charge head first
into the throws of battle!
[CARDIA]
You guys.
[SAINT] If it pleases you, I'd
like to join as well, my lady.
[FRAN]
You're back!
[IMPEY laughs]
You're late to the party!
Where have you been?
We've all been worried sick!
Saint.
I'm going, too!
Are you sure?
[DELACROIX]
Well, generally speaking,
battles between humans
are none of my concern.
But, Helsing!
Don't try to fool
yourself into thinking
I've forgiven your debt!
That said, I like
Cardia quite a bit.
Besides, we've
already established
that when this is over,
your life belongs to me!
I think it's best to
keep a watchful eye.
And so... I'll fight with you!
You're becoming very brave.
[DELACROIX]
Don't you make fun of me!
Thank you, Drac.
[DELACROIX]
Uh.
Uh-huh.
Princess. Is there anything
you'd like to say?
Thank you all.
I've only made it this far
because I had all
of you by my side.
I am in your debt.
But our work's not done.
Help me cross the finish line.
[VICTORIA] Gentlemen, mighty
soldiers of the British Army,
today we march bravely towards
the enemy's stronghold
at St. Paul's Cathedral.
A diversion force will
launch a frontal assault.
At the same time, another force
will infiltrate from the rear.
Thus we will divide their troops
and weaken their defenses.
[VICTORIA] Men, I know you all
have your reasons for fighting.
For this country. For your
families. Or for yourselves.
That said, I beg this
of each and every man
who stands ready for combat.
Today, right here and now,
act as the sword of justice
for Alexandrina Victoria!
Together let us reclaim
the pride of this nation!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[CARDIA]
It's starting.
I don't know what will happen.
I don't know what awaits us
at the end of the battle.
But I know this:
My friends are here.
And I wanna fight for them.
Because I'm not alone.
From now on, no more running.
Charge!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
The battle's begun.
We should all say
a little prayer
Finis doesn't find a way to
outsmart us this time around.
Tell me, Lupin.
The Queen's advisor,
is he not a friend of yours?
Now's not the time for that.
The battle's already underway.
Let's get to work.
[LUPIN]
Right!
[chuckling]
I'm waiting for you, Sister.