[BOTH gasp]
[knocking]
Hope you're hungry because
breakfast is-- Uh.
Well, look at that.
Take it easy, Sisi.
I know, I'm hungry, too!
Don't worry. I haven't
forgotten you.
[IMPEY]
Here.
So did you sleep all right?
[gasps]
About that...
There's a problem with
our household items.
She melts everything
she touches,
so she'll need a new pillow.
[chuckles]
[IMPEY]
And utensils, too!
You can't eat sandwiches
for every meal.
I am a genius chef, you know.
Eventually, I'd like to
show off my cooking skills.
The sandwiches you made
for dinner were delicious.
I really enjoyed them.
I didn't realize that you
were such a good cook.
You're the best, Cardia!
Like an angel in the flesh!
Marry me!
If you touch me, you'll melt.
[IMPEY yelping]
[LUPIN, IMPEY sigh]
Love is never
without its obstacles.
[LUPIN chuckles]
[SAINT] You all sound
like you're having fun.
[LUPIN]
Saint? You're back.
Saint?
[IMPEY] There's one other guy
we work with. His name is Saint.
[LUPIN]
He'll show up sooner or later.
[gasps]
Welcome to my mansion.
The name's Saint-Germain.
It's a pleasure to make your
acquaintance, dear Cardia.
The truth is, I've been waiting
for you for a very long time.
Really? Waiting for me?
Hey! No hitting on Cardia!
Like you're one to talk.
[chuckles]
[SAINT]
Uhh...
[chuckles]
[LUPIN]
Saint has some strange tastes,
but he does a lot to
support our efforts here.
Nobility is so boring.
Right? Right!
He's so bored that he
even takes in terrorists!
Come on! I told you,
I was framed!
[IMPEY chuckles]
[gasps]
[FRAN]
Uh.
I used to be employed
by the government.
But I just did research.
Fran here was the
Head Royal Alchemist,
basically an elite
among the elites!
I'm not an elite anymore.
I'm on the run from
the government.
So you quit? But why?
[gasps]
Oh, uh.
Uh, well, everybody
has a thing or two
they don't wanna
talk about, right?
The question is this:
What is our next
move going to be?
We successfully stole the
Horologium away from Twilight.
That was the first
phase of the plan.
So for now, we should
just lie low.
Focus our energy on gathering
information about their network.
[IMPEY]
Hmm...
There's gotta be a way to make
things move a little faster.
We could try kidnapping
the leader of Twilight!
Slug him real good and say,
"No more terrorism, you jerk!"
I'm not so sure that you
and I are strong enough
to get away with that.
Well, we know this
much for certain:
Cardia's with us now.
She can give us some clues
to help us on our way.
[CARDIA]
Huh?
[FINIS]
What a disappointment.
I can't believe you let some
petty thief steal our prey.
How far the Royal Family's
personal guard has fallen.
Things certainly have changed.
Wouldn't you agree,
Your Majesty?
If you had disclosed
more accurate information
about the monster
in the first place,
then none of this
would've ever happened.
Surely you would
agree with that.
Finis, leader of Twilight.
[FINIS laughs]
What a hypocrite!
I'd say keeping secrets
is your forte!
While London prospers
on all fronts,
so many have shed
blood in the shadows.
Humans. And those
not quite human.
How many filthy,
unspeakable jobs
do you think we've accepted
on your behalf, My Queen?
In any case, you can forget
all about this mission.
Our soldiers are on the move.
They'll recover our
prey soon enough.
Are you telling me you've set
those ignoble men of yours
loose in my fair city?
Before you turn your ire on me,
remember, we wouldn't be here
if it weren't for the
failure of your dogs.
Perhaps a meeting to
discuss your shortcomings
as a leader is required.
Finis.
You may think you have
me under your thumb,
but I want you to
remember something.
You were born in this
country, and as such,
I still consider you one
of my precious children.
When a child starts
to misbehave,
it is his mother's
duty to punish him.
Do keep that in mind, Finis.
[FRAN]
Thank you.
Well, Fran? Did you
learn anything?
The poison inside of her body
is a result of the Horologium.
Is it possible we can
remove it somehow?
[FRAN]
No.
I can't recommend that.
I sort of predicted this, but...
Cardia, I don't hear a
heart beat inside of you.
I can't be sure,
but it's entirely possible
your heart has been lost.
I don't have a... heart?
[FRAN]
That's not entirely accurate.
What keeps you alive is the
eternally-beating heart,
the Horologium itself.
It has taken the
place of your heart.
Well! Cardia, let's go to town!
You mean now?
Hey, there's no time
like the present, right?
You may proceed!
Baron Gilford Dudley and party.
Well done!
Won't you be seen?
We're safe once we've
passed the inspection.
[LUPIN] The Yard is
probably short staffed.
Their resources have
been diminished
due to the recent
string of thefts
targeting noble households.
[IMPEY]
Oh. That flashy thief, right?
It's not me.
[FRAN]
Well, this is my stop.
[CARDIA]
You're not coming with us?
As a matter of fact,
there's something
I need to pick up.
Hey. You ready?
What? I'm staying with Cardia!
Have you already forgotten you
promised to help me out today?
[IMPEY whines]
Since it's the two of us,
how about we treat
ourselves to a little date?
A date?
[CARDIA]
There are so many people,
both inside and
outside of the gate.
Did my father really
commit terrorist acts here?
[LUPIN]
Yes. Sadly, there is no doubt.
[CARDIA]
What if...?
What if a terrorist attack
were to happen right now?
[LUPIN] A lot of people
would die, Cardia.
You see? That's why
we have to act fast.
So!
Next, I'll take you to the
busiest place in London Town!
[CARDIA]
This is a casino?
Yeah. How did you know?
I read about them.
People come here
to get more money.
[LUPIN] That's not all
you can get here though.
The casino is an
underground trade show,
for all kinds of information.
[CARDIA]
Gathering information?
I hope I wasn't in the way.
In the way?
[CARDIA]
Since I can't do anything,
I can't talk to people
like you can, Lupin.
[LUPIN laughs]
You are a woman of few words,
but I wouldn't worry
about that too much.
The real reason we're here
is because I thought
it might make for a
charming change of pace.
[CARDIA] Why are you
doing all of this for me?
[LUPIN]
Huh?
You, Fran, and Impey have all
been so very kind to me.
But I... don't know why.
You saw Sisi. His leg.
[CARDIA]
Mh-hm.
Apparently, some complete
stranger decided to lopp it off.
Impey brought him home with him,
and made him that leg.
He was crying like a
baby the entire time.
His love may be
a one-way street...
...but Sisi is alive today
because of what Impey did.
You see, Cardia, the truth is,
it's the exact same with you.
You may not have a heart,
but that doesn't mean
you're not alive.
The way I see it, you're
no different than us.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's good.
And besides, a heart doesn't
really start beating
until you find the
person you love!
[CARDIA]
Huh?
[LUPIN] Whether you're a man or
a woman, when you fall in love,
all you wanna do is
touch that person.
When you hold them
and you feel their warmth
against your body...
...this starts to beat.
I want to touch.
[LUPIN]
Uh.
[CARDIA]
Earlier when we spoke,
you said you would
grant me a wish.
And so, I would
like to touch you.
To know what it's like
to feel your warmth.
Um. That is... simply one
hell of a pick-up line.
Pick-up line?
Never mind that.
I completely understand.
I swear on my name,
Arséne Lupin,
right here, I will grant your
wish no matter the cost.
I'll save the kiss until then.
Lupin?
Cardia. We're leaving now.
[IMPEY]
Oh.
[IMPEY chuckles]
[IMPEY]
Beautiful women are the best!
I'm all done.
Hm?
[IMPEY]
[LUPIN]
Twilight!
[OPERATIVE B]
Huh?!
What?
[OPERATIVE C]
They're gone?
[bang]
[CARDIA yelps]
[LUPIN]
The bastards flanked us.
[OPERATIVES yelp]
[groans]
[VAN]
Don't move.
They're just salt shells, but
they will hurt if they hit you.
Arsène Lupin.
I don't think we've
met yet, Pretty Boy.
Well, you're not quite
as pretty as me.
Give me the monster now.
Don't try to play
the fool, Lupin,
I know you stole
Twilight's prey from them.
Just hand it over, all right?
I'm sorry, my friend,
but I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
Wait, the monster you're
looking for is me.
Whatever you do,
don't hurt Lupin.
Hey! Cardia!
Wait, you... you're the monster?
[FRAN]
Get down, guys!
Let's go! Come on! Hurry!
Thanks a lot. Cardia,
come on, we should-- Uh!
It's easier to run like this.
Fine.
Just... don't fall down.
[VAN]
Hmph.
[ALL gasp]
Come on! Quick, get in!
[IMPEY]
Did we lose them?
[LUPIN]
For now.
Not only did that guy
know exactly who I am,
but he put out a net.
We should assume he
knows our escape route.
If anyone could, it'd be him.
[LUPIN]
Huh?
[CARDIA]
Fran, do you know that man?
[FRAN] Yeah. I saw him back
when I lived at the palace.
[LUPIN]
Palace?
[ALL gasp]
[crash]
Cardia, you okay? Talk to me.
Yes. Thanks.
[gasps]
Lupin! Cardia!
That's him all right.
He used to be a
member of Twilight.
They called him
"The Human Weapon."
His name is Abraham Van Helsing.
[VAN]
Woman.
What do they mean when
they call you a monster?
Do you carry the
jewels inside you?
The famed jewels
of the Horologium?
My name is Cardia.
I am the daughter
of Issac Beckford.
You're Isaac
Beckford's daughter?
I see. In that case,
you'll make excellent bait.
[FRAN]
Wait.
It sounds like you must
be planning to use her
in an attempt to make some
kind of deal with Twilight.
Tell us what
you're really after.
[VAN]
I have only one target in mind.
The leader of Twilight. Finis.
I promise you this:
I'll make him pay for the
atrocities he's committed
upon the people of this city.
This woman...
...she is an important
pawn in my plan.
[FRAN] In that case,
I have an offer for you.
A better way.
Work with us.
[IMPEY]
Huh?
[VAN]
Work with you?
[FRAN] If you consider
both of our objectives,
working together should benefit
you as much as it would us.
[IMPEY] Whoa! Hang on, Fran!
Think about what you're saying!
Hey. It sounds good to me.
[IMPEY]
Huh?!
Even if we should escape,
it won't change anything.
But if you were to
join forces with us,
we would definitely
be powerful enough
to go up against Twilight.
I'd say it's a win-win.
I see. Wait, really?
What do ya say?
I refuse. This
conversation is over.
Come, woman.
Lupin.
I'm sorry, but I
can't allow a man
who would turn down our offer
to escort her anywhere.
Clearly you don't have the sense
to be entrusted
with such a task.
[VAN]
Suit yourself.
No!
[gunshot]
Lupin.
Nice work!
A special trick of mine.
What do you think?
My gun. Tell me how.
Oh, you want me to
reveal how I did it?
I put sticky putty on a ball
I stole from the casino
and stuffed it in the
muzzle of your gun
when you weren't looking.
[IMPEY]
When did you do that?
[LUPIN] While my
perceptive assistant here
was talking up a storm.
Anyway, if you want,
the offer still stands.
Our goal is to stop Twilight.
But we don't have the man-power
to face them alone.
If we had someone
like you on our side,
that might change the equation.
[VAN]
You're very honest.
But the way I see it,
you three need me a heck of
a lot more than I need you.
[FRAN]
If you join us,
we'd be able to
pull off operations
none of us could ever do alone.
The more our enemy
comes to despise us,
the thicker our red
thread of fate grows.
I can guarantee that.
Finis will reveal himself
to us, without a doubt.
I'll ask again.
Do you want to work together?
[sighs]
[VAN]
Fine.
You've got yourself a deal.
Victor Frankenstein.
Huh? Wait. You know my name?
Yes, of course I do.
How could I not
remember the name
of the former Head
Royal Alchemist?
[chuckles]
Well, guys,
if that's that, can we
consider the matter resolved?
So does this mean
he's one of us now?
[LUPIN]
Hm?
Yeah. Well, I hope so, at least.
This guy's got some very
complicated motivations.
[CARDIA] I feel like his cold
eyes could hold me prisoner.
Because when I look
deep inside them,
I see a sad color
in their depths.
Why is he crying inside?
I wonder, what is he
hiding in his heart?
--Ha!
--[IMPEY] Whoa...
I knew you would
figure it out, Fran!
Now I can really show off
my expert skills as a chef!
This is great. Thanks.
You're welcome, Cardia.
Oh, yeah. May I?
[LUPIN, IMPEY yelp]
I would give anything
to understand
how this dress was made.
As far as I can tell, the
material seems fairly normal,
so perhaps there was something
used to coat the surface?
Fran!
[FRAN]
Huh?
Oh! No, I'm sorry!
I didn't mean any harm!
I don't mind.
[SAINT] It looks like
yet another red thread
has become tangled
around him now.