I understand.
Thanks anyway.
[VAN]
Not enough information.
I guess we're going to have to
use the Horologium as bait.
[whistle blowing]
[OFFICER A]
It's the Phantom Thief!
[OFFICER B]
Get him!
[gasps]
Those two have grown
so close to each other.
[IMPEY] I still can't get
that mutt to play with me!
Heh. Sisi. Look at you, boy.
Stop flirting with her already!
[SISI growls]
[IMPEY yelps]
[IMPEY] Ha-ha. Relax, I was
kidding! It was just a joke!
[IMPEY laughs]
Uh, hey. Van.
Oh, right.
Lupin left earlier. Don't
know when he'll be back.
Here have a seat.
If you want breakfast,
there's plenty for you, too.
[VAN]
Your cooking isn't to my taste.
Come on, you haven't
even tried it yet!
Good morning, Van.
Huh? What gives?
[SAINT chuckles]
I almost forgot.
There's an interesting
article in the paper.
[CARDIA] "Phantom thief
under the moon appears.
Flying in the sky and
disappearing like a fog"?
[IMPEY]
Huh. So he's back?
[SAINT]
Uh-huh.
He's following the same pattern,
employing the exact
same methods as before.
There's more to the story, too.
They say he's been targeting
vampire family treasures.
Wait, vampire?
[SAINT] They're a type of
demi-human with remarkable
physical abilities and
incredibly long lifespans.
They're rather mysterious.
And widely feared, as well.
Oh, I see.
I bet you know quite
a bit about them.
Van Helsing the "Hero."
[VAN]
Hmph.
Generally speaking,
vampire treasures are
rather valuable items,
which makes them a
perfect target for theft.
The Yard's been on high alert,
so I wonder how this guy
manages to pull it off.
This Phantom Thief is giving
Lupin a run for his money!
Speak of the Devil
and he will appear.
[CARDIA] Welcome back,
Lupin. How are you?
[IMPEY] That grumpy man in
the glasses is waiting for you.
[LUPIN]
Oh. I see.
I'm glad everyone is
here at the same place.
As a matter of fact,
the timing is spot on.
[BOTH] You want to capture the
train that Finis is riding?
That's right.
He's boarding a train to
London in two weeks time.
It's perfect.
He's going to be inspecting a
war plant on the north side.
This plan will work.
Finis will be all ours
and Twilight won't even
know what hit them.
I'm not saying I'm on board
with Impey's crazy idea,
but I definitely think
this is the fastest way
to get the info
we're looking for.
Not just about Twilight's
terrorist plot,
but about Issac, too.
Count me in! Let's do this!
Well, I certainly didn't think
we'd be hijacking a train.
But it sounds like a
perfect opportunity to me.
I'm curious, how did you
get that information?
That's top secret.
You have an inside source?
[LUPIN chuckles]
I'm the Gentleman
Thief, remember?
There's a reason
they call me that.
There's nothing I
can't steal, Van.
[LUPIN] Whether it's a jewel,
a person, a piece of art,
or classified information.
[LUPIN]
During his inspection,
security will be weakest
when he's on the train.
If we work together,
I know we can pull this off.
That's great, but Cardia should
probably stay here, right?
Huh?
Good point.
Since you're the one they're
after, we have to keep you safe.
It's best if you stay
at the mansion--
[VAN]
No. We should bring her.
It's like you said. Twilight
wants her more than anything.
If the worst comes to fruition,
at least we'll have
an ace in the hole.
I thought we'd come
to an understanding.
I've been crystal clear.
My only objective is
to take out Finis.
If you want my help, then
you will accept my terms.
Your terms?!
I don't know.
I dislike ultimatums.
But Van's strength is critical
to this mission's success.
I'd like to go.
If you're all putting yourselves
in danger like this,
then I should go, too.
Because we're a team.
But, Cardia, it's not safe.
[LUPIN] All right.
You've got yourself a deal.
[IMPEY] Lupin, slow down!
Think about what you're saying!
Just relax.
I will not let Twilight
get their hands on her.
She's going to have to learn
how to take care of herself.
Starting right now,
your training begins.
My training?
The people in this room have
a wide array of abilities.
We have England's
leading Alchemist.
A well-informed noble.
A battle-hardened hero.
A guy who's good with
machines, if nothing else.
Really?
And a gifted thief with
a 100% success rate!
Who better to teach you
how to defend yourself?
What do you say?
[FRAN]
You're right.
Whatever you need, Cardia,
we're here for you.
[SAINT chuckles]
This sounds
perfectly delightful.
[IMPEY]
Hmm...
But I'm still really worried.
Don't be! I'll work hard!
So please! I want you
to be my teacher, Impey!
[sputters]
Teacher?
Well, when you put it that way,
it has a nice ring to it!
Get ready, 'cause Teacher
Impey's gonna whip up
an invention the likes of which
you've never seen before!
[LUPIN] Whatever you're
going to give her
just make sure it's safe.
If it explodes,
there'll be hell to pay.
[FRAN chuckles]
In that case, maybe we
should teach Cardia
how to dress a wound first?
Hey, I'm not some
kinda imbecile!
I'm a genius engineer!
Have a little faith!
[SAINT]
Impey. Get down...
This is foolishness.
[LUPIN] You seem really,
I don't know, alive.
Like you're having lots of fun.
[CARDIA]
Is this fun? I didn't know.
I've learned quite a bit,
but there's just so
much to remember.
I happen to think
that's a good thing.
In my opinion,
keeping busy with work
is a great way to stay
healthy and strong.
But Fran seems like he's
working all the time.
To the point that his
face gets all pale.
[LUPIN chuckles]
That's called working too hard.
We're all set on the intel.
And the inventions we'll need
for the plan are
coming along, too.
Things are looking good.
[IMPEY] And Cardia's training
is progressing really well!
She's already a pro
behind the wheel!
We've been learning
quite a few things, too.
She's a regular expert
on London now.
It's all thanks to you.
[LUPIN]
Well.
Just wait until Van teaches you
everything about martial arts.
So that's why you
asked me here today?
Sorry, but you're
wasting your time.
Oh, no. I have a
proposal for you.
This is the "Phantom
Thief under the moon"
who keeps going after
vampire family treasures.
They're offering
reward money now.
Word on the street
is he'll be targeting
the Adele and Brutus
Firm's auction next.
Cardia, my dear.
As the finishing touch
to your training,
I want you to
capture this thief.
You're serious?
Better than jumping straight
to fighting Twilight, yes?
Plus, we're low on money. We can
definitely use the extra cash.
What? Are we broke?
[FRAN chuckles]
At this rate, it won't be long
before we can't even
afford to buy food.
Wha--? What about Saint?
You're loaded, right?
I did promise I'd
offer my assistance.
But I never said that
I'd spoil you rotten.
Gotcha. Loud and clear.
[FRAN]
All right. Let's see.
His target is a pendant
called Nosferatu's Saber.
"Whoever successfully captures
this target will get"...
...ten million, seriously?
Oh, wow!
And that's dead or alive!
The money's good.
Which means there're going to
be a lot of different parties
making a play.
But, in the end,
we will prevail.
It's time to show us what
you're made of, Cardia.
Right. I'll do my best!
[VAN]
I'll go with you.
[LUPIN]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
That's unexpected.
I didn't think you'd want
to come along with us.
You can't buy ammo if
you don't have any cash.
That is all there is to it.
[LUPIN]
Hmph.
It's settled, then.
[banging]
This item sold for five million
to bidder Number 3 in the back!
[PATRONS gasping]
[IMPEY]
Whoa.
Five million?
[AUCTIONEER A]
And now.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have the attraction
that you are all
undoubtedly here to see.
It belonged to Delacroix
the Vampire King.
This pendant, his most
prized possession of all,
is called Nosferatu's Saber.
[LUPIN] Something's
bothering you, isn't it?
What's really going on here?
Tell me the truth, Van.
Is Twilight--?
Hear me, you foolish humans!
Keep your filthy hands
off that pendant!
[ASSISTANT A gasps]
[PATRONS screaming]
[BOY] This treasure
belongs to my family,
not to you fiends!
He's so young!
I carry the name of my father,
the head of the
Nosferatu family.
I am the vampire known
as Delacroix the 2nd!
[DELACROIX]
I carry the name of my father,
the head of the
Nosferatu family.
I am the vampire known
as Delacroix the 2nd!
A vampire?
[DELACROIX] My family will never
forgive you human beings.
I'll have my revenge,
no matter the cost!
[PATRONS screaming]
His revenge?
[LUPIN]
The Vampire War.
Two years ago, the
British government
started a large-scale operation
with the express intent of
eradicating all vampires.
It was a war in name only.
Really, it was a vampire hunt.
It's what you'd call the dark
history of the British Empire.
[PATRON A]
Monster!
[PATRON B]
Run! He's a monster!
A vampire hunt?
But why? It's so cruel.
You're not a vampire
at all, are you?
No, no. You're
nothin' but a kid!
If you wanna walk out
of here in one piece,
then you'd better come
with us right now.
Look at how he moves.
The kid's a real vampire after
all! Hurry up and kill him!
Got him!
[BOTH yelp]
Get moving. The kid belongs
to me, understand?
[DELACROIX]
It's you.
It's been a long time. Dracula.
How dare you.
How dare you show your
face in front of me!
I hate you more
than all the rest!
I haven't forgotten the
day I let you escape.
I doubt I ever will.
[growls]
[LUPIN]
Van!
[DELACROIX]
Van Helsing!
Let us settle our score
once and for all!
If you want your
chance to finish this,
if you really want me dead,
I'll be waiting for you
where you killed my father!
Hey, Van. Who was that?
[IMPEY]
Van. Wait!
[IMPEY] Well, that turned
into a big scene.
[FRAN] So the Phantom
Thief is a vampire.
And one of their
royalty, no less.
It looks like you
saw this coming.
Sort of, yes.
So Van was really involved
in the Vampire War?
[FRAN]
Yes, he was.
In fact, he was one of
the most valuable members
of Twilight at the time.
There are those who would
attribute England's victory
in the Vampire War
directly to his involvement.
In what way? Tell me.
He killed Delacroix.
He killed the Vampire King
and his entire family.
I honestly have no idea
how the child survived.
The rest of his family's gone,
which means he must've been
alone this whole time.
That's so sad.
I'm pretty sure Van just
went off to pay his debt.
I don't want anyone to die
tonight. He needs our help.
[DELACROIX laughing]
[VAN]
Please! Reconsider this plan!
The vampires have
always been peaceful!
The attack on humanity
was a mistake, Finis!
[FINIS] I couldn't care
less one way or the other.
As long as the British
Empire can show off
its military power to
the rest of the world,
then I couldn't
care less who dies.
You don't mean...
Was the attack fabricated
by the government?
Was it nothing but a false flag?
[FINIS]
So what if it was?
Either way, it doesn't
fundamentally change your job.
[VAN]
I can't do it.
[FINIS]
Oh, I disagree.
If you want your family
safe, you'll comply.
[gasps]
[DELACROIX]
Father? What's wrong?
[gasps]
[VAN]
It's time. I have to end this.
[door opens]
[DELACROIX] I've been
waiting for you. Helsing.
Take arms.
Here, in the same
spot my father died,
I will remove your head
from your shoulders!
[DELACROIX] My father's regret.
My mother's grief.
The anger of my compatriots.
I will avenge them all,
right here and now!
[yells]
Just like old times.
Why did you betray him?
He trusted you, Van!
Do you truly despise me,
Count Dracula?
Never call me that!
Ever since you
murdered my father,
I inherited his name!
I despise you with
all that I am!
Then fight me like you
mean it, Delacroix the 2nd.
[yells]
[IMPEY] Well, this place
has seen better days.
You said you'd take
revenge on all humanity.
Is this all you've got?
[growls] Shut up!
[CARDIA gasps]
You're far too weak.
You can't even defeat me.
[DELACROIX] Don't
underestimate me, Van Helsing!
I've lived my whole
life for this moment!
Humanity's about to
get what it deserves!
Lupin, please!
It'll be fine.
[VAN]
It's over now.
Give up on taking revenge
on human beings. You got it?
[DELACROIX]
You want me to give up?
How could I?
What do I do with this anger?
Where do I put
all of this hatred?
It was you humans!
You took my father away from me!
[VAN screams]
[VAN]
I fulfilled my duty. And yet...
Damn you, Finis.
I will give you
my life, Delacroix.
Wait, what?
[VAN] There is something
I have to do first.
Because of that, I cannot
give you my life right now.
But when my task is
done, you can have it.
You have my word.
All of these people
here are my witnesses.
What sort of game
are you playing, Van?
I don't believe you!
And I will never forgive you!
[VAN]
You don't have to.
I'm the one you despise.
Humanity has
nothing to do with it.
You can have your revenge.
Just leave the
rest of them alone.
[DELACROIX crying]
[CARDIA]
He needs help.
Can we please take this boy
back to the mansion with us?
We can't leave him here.
If we do, he'll be
lonely and afraid.
I know that feeling.
There's not a soul
on this planet
that deserves to be alone.
[CARDIA] Would you like
to come live with us?
I just can't!
I am his grave keeper. I'm
not going to leave him alone.
[VAN]
Keep an eye on me.
[DELACROIX gasps]
When I finish,
you can take my life.
You can have your vengeance.
Then you can finally find
the peace you deserve.
[gasps]
[CARDIA] Do you think
he'll actually come?
You said you wanted to learn
martial arts, didn't you?
I'll teach you what I know.
Huh?
[VAN]
Be warned, I show no mercy.
Not even to women.
Fine by me.
That's very kind. Thanks.
[CARDIA]
The sad color I saw in his eyes
when we first met
hasn't disappeared.
But now I see
something different:
A kindness hiding
just underneath.
Someone else reached out to me.
Now I want to do
the same for him.
But how? I just wanna
help in any way I can.
I'm really glad you're
training her, Van.
Just make sure you're not
too rough on the lady, okay?
[rustling]
[DELACROIX]
Van Helsing, all those promises
that you made to
me back there...
...did you mean them?
Looks like we're having
a welcome party tonight.
You'd better join in, Van!
[VAN]
Sure.