[YUICHIRO]
Every time I close my eyes.
I see the same scene play out.
[MIKAELA] Jeez, would you
quit walking so fast?
Wait up! I'm family!
Don't abandon me, Yu!
[YUICHIRO] I don't have
a family. Leave me alone.
[MIKAELA giggles]
Sorry, no can do!
The director said everyone
from the Hyakuya Orphanage
is family, so shut up
and deal with it.
[YUICHIRO]
Get off'a me!
[KOUTA]
We are a family, aren't we?
[AKO]
Duh! Of course we are, silly!
[AKANE] One big happy family.
Isn't that right, Yu?
[YUICHIRO] Honestly, you guys
are a pain in the butt.
[KIDS laughing]
[YUICHIRO] I see the smiling
faces of my dearest friends.
My family. And then...
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[YUICHIRO] I see their
bloody, lifeless bodies
lying in front of me.
[panting]
Yu, leave us! Get out of here!
[MIKAELA whimpering]
Forget about us! Just go! Hurry.
Mika!
[YUICHIRO] It never fails.
Even after four years.
I'm still haunted by my painful
memories of that night.
[rumbling]
[GUARD 2A] It's the
"Four Horsemen of John!"
What the hell are
you doing here?
Get out of the combat zone,
Private Hyakuya!
That's an order!
[YUICHIRO] Who, me? Run away?
Don't count on it.
The only reason I'm here
is to get revenge
on those bloodsucking freaks.
If I can't handle a
small fry like this one,
then I don't deserve
to take another breath!
Private! Stop!
[TEACHER 2A]
He wasn't using...
[YUICHIRO]
This is a load of crap.
I kill a monster and get
slapped with a suspension?
They should be promoting me,
not making me rot
in this civilian dump!
I'm a soldier, dammit!
[TEACHER clears throat]
Hey!
What're you mumbling
about over there?
Do you have something
you'd like to add?
If so, then let's hear it.
[YUICHIRO sighs]
Hmph.
[TEACHER] Oh! You better
shape up, Hyakuya!
Don't give me any more trouble!
I'll have you suspended!
What? You'd really
kick me outta here?
Awesome!
Well then, I humbly
request suspension.
How dare you?! Enough!
I won't have you mocking me
in front of the class!
Sit down and pay attention!
[YUICHIRO]
What? You got somethin' to say?
[YUICHIRO] "If you continue
to behave uncooperatively,
I will have no choice but to
report you to the army
and extend your suspension".
What?! You gotta be kiddin' me!
That's it!
One more outburst and I'm
sending you straight to the--
Ugh! This sucks!
Let me finish!
Start cooperating.
--[YUICHIRO] Uh...
--[TEACHER panting]
[TEACHER 2A]
Now, where were we? Ah, yes!
[SHINOA] I should also
point out that your suspension
will remain in effect until
you successfully make a friend.
[YUICHIRO]
Uh--?
You heard right.
So play nice and
be a good student.
[YUICHIRO sighs]
[YUICHIRO panting]
But how can you be a human?
Everyone on the surface died!
That what the vamps told you?
I guess I would've done
the same in their shoes.
[GUREN] Heh. Well, it's true
that the virus reduced
the world's population
by about 90%.
And, thanks to the
Trumpets of the Apocalypse,
an army of bizarre
looking monsters
are now roaming the Earth.
But it'll take more than
that to wipe out mankind.
Our resurrection is underway.
[YUICHIRO]
Resurrection?
Yep, and that's not all.
We have plans to make sure our
organization ends up on top.
We're going to
take back the Earth
and gather humanity's
remnants under one banner.
No way. So who are you guys?
Lieutenant Colonel Ichinose.
Call me Guren. I'm with
the Imperial Demon Army.
Kid, how would you
like to come with us
and get back at
those bloodsuckers?
Put this on him.
Tell me. Do you wanna
get back at the vampires?
[panting]
I do.
If you want your revenge,
take my hand.
I'll give you all
the power you need.
More like "take my hand
and I'll ignore you."
You promised me power, Guren,
not a four-year
waste of my time.
[STUDENT 2A]
I'm skipping practice.
[STUDENT 2B] 'Kay! Let's get
ice cream on the way home!
[YUICHIRO sighs]
[SHINOA]
"Wait up! Mind if I come along?
I could really go for
a cone right now."
You just missed a
golden opportunity
to make some new friends.
[YUICHIRO] Are you tryin'
to boss me around?
That's not a good idea.
There's that famous attitude
I've heard about.
According to Lieutenant
Colonel Guren,
you avoid social interaction
'cause you lost your family.
You're too afraid to
engage other people.
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[SHINOA]
You fear making connections,
or letting anyone
get close to you.
Because you're afraid
you may lose them.
It sounds lonely.
Don't you want a girlfriend
or maybe a boy--?
Look. I'm not
afraid of anything,
so quit running your mouth
and get off my back.
I guess you can "engage."
[YUICHIRO] If you won't
shut up, then use your trap
for something useful,
like telling Guren
to put me in the
Vampire Extermination Unit!
I'm ready.
Give me the chance to make
the fangs bleed for a change.
Here. He thought
you might say that.
So the Lieutenant Colonel
told me to give this to you.
[YUICHIRO] Now that's
what I'm talking about.
I knew he hadn't forgotten me.
"Cherry-boys that
can't make a friend
or a girlfriend...
[GUREN]
...don't belong in our army.
Go out, make one,
then introduce them to me.
Of course, I'm not
gonna hold my breath.
[YUICHIRO growls]
[YUICHIRO]
Who does he think he is?
You can both go to hell!
[YUICHIRO]
What are you doing?
Haven't you annoyed me enough?
Stop following me around.
Sorry, no can do.
I am your Army Surveillance
Officer, after all.
[YUICHIRO sighs]
Any violation of army
guidelines will be reported.
[YOICHI]
Would you please stop?
[SHINOA, YUICHIRO]
Huh?
[YAMANAKA] Stop what? I'm just
asking you to be a pal
and lend me some
money for a snack.
That a problem, wimp?
[YOICHI grunts]
Sucks to be him.
Whatever. I'm outta here.
I'm disappointed
in you, Private.
You won't make any
friends if you keep
turning your back
on people in need.
[YAMANAKA]
What's the hold up?
You wanna be friends
with us, don't'cha?
Come on. Hand it over!
Or I'll sick the vampires on ya.
What? You want me
to kick your ass?
[YUICHIRO]
Hey. Give it a rest, ya punks.
[BULLIES]
Huh?
Why? Who in the
hell are you?
What's this? Showing compassion?
You might just prove
your file wrong.
[YUJI]
Punks, huh? We got a tough guy.
You wanna play the
hero, is that it?
All right, then.
After we beat your face in,
you can be our new errand boy.
[YUICHIRO] Awesome. See,
this is why I love bullies.
Huh?
They're simple and stupid.
[BULLIES]
Huh?
Okay. Wanna fight? Let's go.
[YAMANAKA growls]
What?
Oh. I should have
mentioned this before.
Fighting civilians is prohibited
and will extend your suspension.
[gasps]
Huh?!
Running errands
for those jerks.
Why me, man?
[sighs]
Um, I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
You've got hands.
Help us carry stuff.
Ha! I'm only here
to observe, sorry.
Figures.
Please. Forgive me.
Quit apologizing
every two seconds!
It's really annoying!
What's your problem, anyway?
Why do you let those jerk
wads bully you like that?
[YOICHI]
I'm not being bullied.
[YUICHIRO]
Oh, right. So he just happened
to use your face
as a stepping stool.
[YOICHI] No, it's true!
They really aren't bullying me.
[YUICHIRO]
What?
Yeah.
Y'see, I have a favor I
need to ask of Yamanaka.
And, well, getting on his
good side isn't exactly easy.
Which one was Yamanaka?
Seriously? Are you
really that dense?
Yamanaka's the guy who
sucker punched you in the face.
Oh, him.
So, what? You his fan boy?
[YOICHI]
No, not exactly.
I failed the Imperial
Demon Army's entrance exam.
I've always wanted to join them.
But Yamanaka -- he passed
with flying colors.
He's even being considered
for the Moon Demon Company.
No freakin' way!
That guy? But they
wouldn't even let me in!
Ugh! Guren, you jerk!
You'll pay for this!
So, I was hoping he'd
have some connections.
If he knows the right people,
maybe I could get
another shot at
the entrance exam.
I know I'm not
much of a soldier,
and there's no place for
weaklings in the army.
But...
What?
If I join, I can get
revenge for my sister.
[YUICHIRO]
Revenge?
[grunts]
[YOICHI] My sister was
killed by a vampire.
She was trying to protect me.
[whimpers]
I froze.
I wanted to save her,
but I couldn't. And, so...
Uh-- Ah!
Moron.
If you had helped her,
you'd be dead, too.
Then she would've
died for nothing.
But--
[YUICHIRO]
No buts.
Lemme give you some advice.
Don't join the army.
Remember. Your sister
doesn't want revenge.
She's gone.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO]
Besides, a wimpy kid like you
would only get in the way.
We need to kill the fangs,
not feed them.
Uh--
[grunts]
[YOICHI grunts, sighs]
[gasps]
[STUDENTS scream]
[ANNOUNCEMENT 2A]
Emergency alert!
All students and faculty
members be advised.
A vampire has escaped from
the nearby Bioresearch facility.
Why would a vampire
wanna come here?
[YOICHI] If it's in the school,
we're as good as dead!
Would you two be quiet?
[ANNOUNCEMENT 2A]
Vampires regain their strength
by drinking blood.
Both of you! Get out
of here, quickly!
I'll call the Moon Demon Company
in to take care of the--
[YUICHIRO]
Screw them!
[SHINOA, YOICHI gasp]
I'll kill the sucker
with my own two hands!
[SHINOA]
What?!
Then he'll have
to let me join!
I'm gonna make Guren
eat his words!
[SHINOA]
Hey, Wait a minute!
That's suicide!
You idiot.
[SHINOA grunts]
Huh?
Whoa!
Double idiot!
[STUDENT 2D] The Demon Army
said the city was totally safe!
[STUDENT 2E]
Hey! Shut up and walk!
Let me get through!
[YUICHIRO panting]
[STUDENT 2F screams]
[VAMPIRE 2B gasps]
[YAMANAKA]
I-It's you!
[YUICHIRO]
Hm?
[gasping]
[YUICHIRO] It's been awhile
since I've seen a vamp.
I'm gonna kill you.
For my family!
Human trash.
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[groans]
[grunts]
[STUDENT 2F groans]
Help.
Yamanaka! Take this girl
and get out of here!
Hurry!
Huh?
[YUICHIRO] You're a
soldier candidate, right?
Hop to it, man!
But, I was lying!
What?
[YAMANAKA] I thought if
I told everyone that,
then they would fear me.
[VAMPIRE 2B] Pesky brat.
Know your place, livestock.
[VAMPIRE 2B]
If you're intent on interfering,
then I won't waste time
playing with my food.
[gasps]
[VAMPIRE 2B grunts]
[growls]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
--[YUICHIRO grunts]
--[VAMPIRE 2B gasps]
[VAMPIRE 2B] Hmph. You might
think you're tough,
but there's no way
you'll ever defeat me.
I'm going to be unstoppable.
Once I've healed myself
by drinking her blood.
No!
[YOICHI panting]
[VAMPIRE 2B, YOICHI grunt]
Are you okay?
Yoichi!
[VAMPIRE 2B]
You little...!
[YOICHI gasps]
[VAMPIRE 2B yells]
[YUICHIRO grunting]
[growls]
Yoichi. Good job!
That was impressive!
Wow. Thank you.
But, that's what friends
are for, right?
[gasps]
I've had enough
of you, human!
[yells]
[gasps] Hyakuya!
[YUICHIRO groans]
[chuckles] Nice try.
Did you really think
this would kill me?
Give me a break.
I'm stronger than that.
I think I've earned a
little snack for the road.
[gasps, groans]
I'm sorry. You were saying?
But how? How do you
have a cursed weapon?
Tsk, tsk. How the mighty
have fallen. You're pathetic.
[GUREN]
And speaking of pathetic.
What were you thinking?
How'd you plan to kill it with a
normal blade and no enchantment?
Or were you hoping I'd come
to save your sorry ass?
Whatever! I had it.
I was about to make my move.
Right.
[YUICHIRO]
It's true!
Uh-huh.
[GUREN]
Then again.
I have to admit you did
pretty well, for a kid.
Thanks to you, the overall
damage was minimal.
On top of that, you saved
all your friends at school.
[YUICHIRO] Holy crap!
That's the Moon Demon Company!
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not interested
in making friends!
Tch. Hey! Now you've
seen what I can do!
I can kill vampires
with the best of 'em!
So make me a part of
the company, already!
Sorry, but I make
it a strict policy
not to work with lone wolves.
--[SHINOA giggles]
--[GUREN] Hm?
[SHINOA]
That's pretty funny coming from
the biggest lone wolf
in the Demon Army.
Huh? Did you say something?
No, sir.
Anyway, the rules Shinoa
gave you remain the same.
If you can't make a
friend at this school,
then I won't have you joining--
What is it with you trying
to force me to make friends?
It's not like it's gonna help
you kill more vampires!
[YOICHI]
Oh, thank goodness!
Huh?
Hyakuya! You're alive!
I thought you'd died!
[YOICHI yelping]
[YUICHIRO, YOICHI grunt]
Who's that?
[SHINOA]
His friend, apparently or lover.
Uh? Hyakuya? What's wrong?
Somebody call an ambulance!
Now that he's met
your requirements,
you have to keep up your
end of the bargain,
Lieutenant Colonel.
[gasps] What?
Are you kidding me?
[YUICHIRO]
Every time I close my eyes,
I see the same scene play out.
I see the smiling faces
of my dearest friends.
My family. And then...
[MIKAELA] Whew, you had
us worried there, Yu.
But I'm glad you
made a new friend.
[YUICHIRO]
But, how are you guys still--?
Now we can stop
worrying about you.
Don't you get it?
We don't want you
to live for revenge.
You're way too nice
to go through that.
Listen.
You need to take good care
of your new friend, okay?
Well, we've gotta get going.
[YUICHIRO gasps] Uh--! Hey!
What do you mean you're going?
Mika, please don't leave me!
Wait! Come back! Mika!
[gasps]
[YOICHI gasps]
Hyakuya! Thank goodness.
Look, Shinoa! He finally
managed to wake up!
[gasps] It's about time.
[SHINOA]
I have good news.
As of today, you're
officially assigned
to the Vampire
Extermination Unit.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
[YOICHI]
Congrats, Yu! That's awesome!
[SHINOA]
I almost forgot!
Your enlistment
was also accepted.
Welcome to the army, Yoichi.
The two of you made quite an
impression on your comrades.
You put your lives on the line,
and fought bravely,
for people you don't even know.
Gentlemen, welcome to
Moon Demon Company.
[YOICHI]
Hm.
From now on, you're one of us.
[YOICHI]
C'mon. Bring it in, buddy!
[YUICHIRO sighs]
This is so stupid.
[YUICHIRO]
Fine.
Happy?
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End.
"The Demon in Your Heart."