[crashing]
[clattering, clinking]
[YOICHI whimpers]
[gasps]
[YOICHI grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
Don't come out from under
here, no matter what.
[gasps]
[TOMOE grunts]
[YOICHI]
Wait, sister!
[grunts]
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[TOMOE whimpering]
[RENE] Hey, Lacus.
Headquarters is checking in.
They want an update.
[LACUS]
Mm?
Now of all times. It figures.
[YOICHI whimpers]
It's always when I'm in
the middle of eating.
[YOICHI whimpers]
No. This can't be happening.
[gasps]
So, here we are, Yoichi.
Reliving your most
traumatic memory
in detail, right down to the
blood splatters on the floor.
Huh? Tomoe. You're alive!
[YOICHI grunts]
Because of you, she's dead now.
[YOICHI gasps]
[MIRAI]
Is that you, brother?
[KIMIZUKI]
I'm sorry, Mirai.
I didn't mean to wake you up.
[MIRAI]
You didn't.
How're you feeling?
[MIRAI] Not too bad. I think
it's gonna be a good day for us.
I do, too.
[KIMIZUKI]
I bet you're hungry.
How 'bout I scrounge up
something for you to eat. Kay?
[MIRAI] Brother. Why don't you
leave me here to fend for myself
so you can move on
with your life?
Don't start with this.
Taking care of you is my duty.
[MIRAI] But... if things don't
change, you'll end up dead, too.
No "buts," Mirai. I'm gonna
make sure we both survive.
You don't mean that. Not really.
At night, I hear you cry...
...about how much
you want to leave.
You've grown to hate me.
You wish I'd just die already.
[gasps]
[KIMIZUKI]
Why... Why would you say that?
Because despite how
noble you try to be,
deep down, you're
a selfish human
who only thinks of himself.
Isn't that right,
Shiho Kimizuki?
Now I get it. You're the demon.
Bingo.
But I was right about
your thoughts, wasn't I?
I've seen every shameful thing
that's floated through
your little brain.
I wonder what your sister would
say if she knew the truth.
Shut the hell up!
[GUREN]
Interesting.
[KIMIZUKI gasping]
At least one of them appears
to be putting up a fight.
[MIKAELA]
It's good to see ya.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Even if you did
run off and leave us
to die with the vampires.
It's not a good idea to
imitate people I care about.
[MIKAELA]
Well then.
I thought I'd be able
to shake you up
by touching on a sore spot.
But you don't appear
the least bit rattled.
Now I wonder. Why is that?
You're not the first demon who's
tried to mess with my head.
So, just cut the crap and
hand over your power already.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[MIKAELA exhales]
Mika!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[ASURAMARU]
Oh, I see what's going on.
You managed to defeat a
low-ranking demon like Myo-o.
And now you think
you've got what it takes
to tame a being
with actual power.
I could possess
your heart and mind
without the slightest effort.
You talk big.
But I'm not giving up until
I've got a contract with you.
If you've got so much strength,
then prove it to me!
[ASURAMARU]
Hm.
You've taken up my blade in
search of a demon's might.
The question is why.
I want revenge!
[ASURAMARU] Because you've
lost someone important to you?
That's right. I lost the
only family... I ever had.
[ASURAMARU]
That must have been difficult.
Very well, then. I can see
the desire for revenge
burning inside you.
I can offer you unlimited
power to achieve it.
[YUICHIRO]
Yes!
[AKANE] But it's not quite
that simple. Sorry, Yu.
[YUICHIRO gasping]
To get our strength, you'll
have to give yourself over
and succumb to your
desire for vengeance.
[ASURAMARU] Your unjustly
murdered friend is right.
I'd have to possess you to give
you the kind of power you want.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
No, wait!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[MIKAELA]
Yu.
[gasps]
You're not gonna run off
and ditch us again, are you?
[AKANE] You can't just
abandon your family.
[TAICHI] Brother Yu would
never do something so dumb.
[FUMIE]
Now that we're reunited,
say you'll live here
with us forever!
[CHIHIRO]
Yes, stay with us. We miss you.
[grunts]
Ah, there it is. Your weakness.
You have love in your heart, and
that's what's holding you back.
[YUICHIRO grunts]
We worship desire.
We can't stand love.
Yoichi, Kimizuki, Shinoa...
Your new friends.
Forget about them.
You can't become a
champion of revenge
if you're worried about others.
But, my friends...
[MIKAELA] Don't you think
it's unfair that we're dead
and you're making a new family?
[AKANE] You left us behind
and now you've moved on.
Going to school, training,
and making new friends.
You've almost managed
to completely forget
about us, haven't you?
I have not! I've
never forgotten!
Then forget your new
friends and stay with us.
Remember, we're the only
family you've ever had.
Shut your mouth.
It's the only way you'll get
the strength to avenge us.
Stop it.
You're gonna submit
yourself to revenge now.
Go to hell! Stop trying
to confuse me, you bastard!
[YUICHIRO] I don't just need
your strength to get revenge.
There's more to it.
My aim is bigger.
I want enough power to protect
everything and everyone!
[panting]
[ASURAMARU] This is
the trouble with humans.
Your emotions are
too complicated.
Love for your friends
and fear for their safety
compete against your
desire for revenge.
[ASURAMARU] I like you.
Your spirit is strong.
I'll agree to follow you
as long as it stays that way.
--But if I detect weakness
--[gasps]
in your heart for even a moment,
I'll take over
your body and soul.
All right. I guess that's fair.
[ASURAMARU]
My name is Asuramaru.
If you need power, all you
have to do is call for me.
[YUICHIRO]
Asuramaru.
[ASURAMARU] Oh, and since
you're going to be my master,
let me give you some
insider information as a gift.
[YUICHIRO]
Information?
[ASURAMARU] There's something
odd about your composition.
You appear to be human,
but about ten percent of you
is something... different.
Could the humans be doing
strange experiments
on you or something?
Huh? What are
you talking about?
[ASURAMARU] You shouldn't
trust your own kind.
Believe me when I tell you
mankind is more devious
than vampires and
demons combined.
Though, it does feel a little
weird saying that to a human.
Wait. Explain yourself.
What are you suggesting?
[gasps]
[ASURAMARU] Very well.
The contract is now complete.
From this day forward,
I shall lend you my
strength and abilities.
Open your eyes.
Fan the flames of desire
that burn inside of you
and forge a bloodstained
path in this world.
Yuichiro Hyakuya!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[GUREN] You're awake.
How ya feeling, Yu?
I'm okay. Uh?
Heh. I beat the demon.
[KIMIZUKI]
I wouldn't get too cocky.
You took your sweet time
subjugating the damned thing.
[YUICHIRO]
You got a Cursed Gear, too?
[KIMIZUKI]
Of course I did.
[YUICHIRO]
Hmph.
And Yoichi?
[YUICHIRO gasps]
So, then, who are you?
[TOMOE]
Hm?
You're the one who
called me, Yoichi.
If you want to avenge
your sister's death,
you need a strong set
of Cursed Gear to wield.
Oh, that's right.
I picked up a weapon and was
going to make a contract with--
I see. That's what
you are, a demon.
That's right.
Hmph. It's pretty mean you
chose to look like this.
[TOMOE] Just wait until
you see my true form.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I bet it's pretty nasty.
So, it seems we have
a bit of a problem.
Huh?
I've poured over
your heart and soul.
You wanna strike back
at those who hurt you,
but that desire is too weak.
Your soul is gentle, and kind.
You have great love for others.
These are all qualities
that I despise.
Wait. Maybe you
should look deeper.
'Cause I do want
to avenge my sister.
You lie. In fact, the
strongest feeling you have
is the relief that you
survived the attack.
No. That's not true.
Not to mention you'd
make a terrible fighter.
You're afraid of conflict,
and the thought of your friends
and family getting hurt.
You're weak. You don't have
the courage to take a life.
How are you supposed
to get revenge
if you aren't
capable of killing?
What I really mean
is you're a coward.
Just a child without
a backbone. A weakling.
[YOICHI gasps]
[whimpering]
But there is one way
you can bring hell
upon those who
murdered your sister.
Give me your body. Forever!
[gasps]
[YOICHI yelps]
[screaming]
[YOICHI whimpering]
You don't even have the
guts to fight for your life.
You wouldn't make
a suitable master.
You're the most pathetic
human being I've ever met.
[YOICHI whimpering]
[KIMIZUKI, YUICHIRO gasp]
[metal scraping]
Aw, man. This is not good.
[GUREN] Looks like Yoichi
didn't have the strength
to overcome possession.
But, I guess having two
outta three students
pass the Black Demon tryout
isn't that bad at all.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
Hey, wait, where'd he go?
[YOICHI] One, two, three,
four little humans all for me.
Dammit, but they've each
got Cursed Gears, too.
Power hungry humans are
such a pain in the ass.
[YOICHI]
My bow.
All right. Now that you two
have both got your Cursed Gear,
it's time for
your first mission.
There's a human-eating demon
loose somewhere in this room.
Yu, Kimizuki.
It's up to you guys
to deal with it.
Show that bastard
who's in control.
They'll be my appetizers.
Then the real feast will begin!
Yoichi!
[YUICHIRO, KIMIZUKI grunt]
[YOICHI grunts]
[YOICHI laughs]
[sighs]
Well, great.
Looks like this demon is
coming at us with full force.
Yoichi must've just been
a snack to whet its appetite.
[SHINOA]
Lieutenant Colonel!
[GUREN]
Hm?
May I share my opinion?
Please don't. Quiet!
[SHINOA] This situation's
getting out of control!
[YUICHIRO]
Hey, Guren!
[GUREN grunts]
How are we supposed
to deal with this?
[YUICHIRO yelps]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
Yoichi is still one of us!
Look at him! Your classmate's
body is just a vessel now.
The only way to save
Yoichi is to destroy it.
What the hell, man?
There's no way I'm gonna
kill one of my friends.
Don't you get soft on me!
This is the Moon Demon Company.
Extermination is your job!
Or are you guys all talk
and just here to play
around with Cursed Gear?
[YUICHIRO grunts]
If you wanna get
killed, that's on you.
But that monster's not
your friend anymore.
[KIMIZUKI]
Dammit!
[KIMIZUKI grunting]
[GUREN] If you're serious
about using those weapons,
then show me you've got
what it takes to be a soldier.
[YUICHIRO]
Dammit, Yoichi.
Sorry, but... you're going down!
[gasps]
What the hell was that?
--[KIMIZUKI] Yu!
--[gasps]
[KIMIZUKI]
Hmph.
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[YOICHI laughs]
[KIMIZUKI grunting]
[KIMIZUKI yells]
[BOTH grunting]
Let Yoichi go, you monster.
He's one of us!
[YUICHIRO yelps]
Yes!
[GUREN]
You Idiot!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Don't let up!
The demon's not inside
the weapon anymore,
it's in his body!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[YUICHIRO yelps]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
Don't do it! We can
still save him!
[gasps]
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
Interesting. You won't touch me
because of the body I'm in?
Yoichi! I know you're in there!
Don't let this stupid demon get
the best of you. Snap out of it!
We're supposed to kill
vampires together, remember?
[SHINOA grunts]
[SHINOA]
Lieutenant Colonel.
These boys are going to
get themselves killed!
They're not ready for this.
Please, don't make them kill
Yoichi. He's their friend!
[GUREN]
Aww.
You always act like
you're so cool,
but you've got a soft spot
for these two problem students.
You've gotten attached,
haven't you?
[SHINOA]
Lieutenant Colonel!
Why don't you step in
and kill him, then?
That'll save the others
from being racked with guilt.
[SHINOA sighs]
Oh, I see.
You've got no intention
of getting your
hands dirty, either.
Let me guess, your just
"too cute" for this as well.
Yoichi, get yourself together.
You're strong enough
to beat this thing!
It's too late.
[YOICHI]
Now die.
[grunts]
[YUICHIRO]
Do it.
I won't kill a comrade,
but I won't abandon one, either.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO] If Yoichi's
still alive in there,
then you won't be
able to shoot me.
[laughs]
You and I are alike
in that way.
When you've watched your
family die in front of you...
...there's no way that you
could ever kill a friend.
[gasps] Are you crazy?
[SHINOA grunts]
[sighs]
You'll have to come
back or shoot me!
Snap out of it, Yoichi!
[YOICHI]
Fool.
Die.
Yoichi!
Are you gonna
stay under that bed
and watch your sister be killed
or take charge and stop it?
[YOICHI]
Uh-- Uh...
This is your last chance
to take control.
[whimpering]
[TOMOE]
Yoichi, listen!
No matter what happens,
don't come out from under here.
I'm sorry. But I can't stay.
No more hiding. I'm not gonna
run away from my fears anymore!
That's why I need the ability
to protect those I care about.
I want to be able to
keep them safe from harm.
Only then can I make sure
nothing like this
ever happens again.
Give me that power, you demon!
[YOICHI whimpering]
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO]
Hmph.
[YOICHI grunting]
[KIMIZUKI, SHINOA gasp]
[YOICHI crying]
[YUICHIRO]
Whoa.
No way.
Did, he just beat it?
[crying]
[YUICHIRO] That's enough.
You did a good job.
I... shot at you.
[YOICHI crying]
[footsteps]
[GUREN]
Hm.
[YUICHIRO yelps]
You took way too
long to get back!
What the hell?
But, why would you kick
me for that, Guren?
[YOICHI]
Yu, are you okay?
[SHINOA]
Did you know
that it would end this way,
Lieutenant Colonel?
What's that? Hell no.
I don't really give a damn
if one of these kids
ends up biting it.
You say that, but you
looked like you were
really starting to sweat there,
towards the end of it.
[GUREN]
Hm.
[YOICHI whimpering]
[YOICHI gasps]
Uh?
[GUREN]
You have a rare gift.
The guilt you felt for
not helping your sister
has kept you from
living your life.
But I think today
you overcame that.
Maybe now you'll be able to
reach your full potential.
[gasps]
You have a new reason to live.
From now on, your job
is to protect the people
who saved your life today.
Forget revenge. Don't get hung
up on something so pointless.
[GUREN]
Same goes for you, idiot.
[YUICHIRO]
Ow.
[YUICHIRO grunts]
Forget about your previous
friends and loved ones.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh? Don't be ridic--
The Moon Demon Company's the
only family you'll have now.
You're gonna put us first,
even before your own life.
Got it?
[GUREN]
The past means nothing.
[gasps]
[GUREN]
It's the future that matters.
Stupid Guren.
[GUREN]
Hmph.
Okay. Well, you've
all got Cursed Gear.
And you almost worked
like a team today.
I suppose we should test
you out on the front lines
to see what you're
really made of.
--Seriously?
--[YOICHI gasps]
[GUREN]
That's right.
We've got intel that suggests
vampires from the Kansai Region
are planning on
reclaiming Shinjuku.
It's our job to
investigate the area.
We're finally gonna
get to hunt vampires!
Um. Shouldn't we have
some more training first?
[KIMIZUKI] We don't even
get a break after all this?
[SHINOA giggles]
[GUREN sighs]
[GUREN] I think these lazy kids
are gonna be the death of me.
[plane engine humming]
[ANNOUNCER] We'll be
arriving in Tokyo shortly.
We expect attacks from the
Japanese Imperial Demon Army
near Ikebukuro,
Shinjuku, and Shibuya.
Please maintain caution.
Did you hear that? Well, Mika?
We're going to Shinjuku first.
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
"Mitsuba's Squad."