Today, we've gathered all nobles
with the progenitor's blood
to address a growing concern.
Humans!
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army
has been ramping up operations
and increasing their
numbers in Northern Tokyo.
This human organization is
killing our brothers...
[MIKAELA]
"Human organization"?
[HOST] ...and flirting
with forbidden enchantments
to increase their power.
According to our intel,
they are once again
experimenting on
the Seraph of the End.
[KRUL]
Hm.
If we allow these humans
to continue to rise
and gain strength,
another plague like the one
that occurred eight years ago
will surely come to pass.
[KRUL]
You needn't worry about that.
Because we're exterminating the
Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
We're going to war!
[CROWD gasps]
To ensure that we continue
to rule this world,
we'll have to slaughter the
greedy livestock resistance
once and for all!
[CROWD cheers]
[MIKAELA]
Extermination.
The Seraph of the End.
Don't worry, Yu. I'm coming
to your rescue soon.
[GUREN snores]
[OFFICER] That's all I have
to report from Block Three, sir.
[rustling, clattering]
[SHINYA] I'm Imperial Demon Army
Major General, Shinya Hiragi.
I'll be covering reports
from the Kansai region.
Several of them concern
suspicious vampire activity,
among other things.
[GUREN snores]
Ichinose!
Hey! Quit sawin' logs!
Uh...? Huh? Ahh...
Are we finally done with
this boring ass meeting?
[TENRI]
Drop the attitude, Guren.
You're not as special
as you might think.
[GUREN]
Sorry, General.
It's just so hard to remember
that when I'm surrounded
by the dullest
personalities in the army.
Is that so?
Well, I can beat the lesson--
Pardon, sir.
Ichinose's attitude is
nothing new to this room.
Now, as I was saying.
[chair clatters]
[GUREN]
I'm takin' off.
You can send me all
of the information later.
Come on, Guren. I can't
defend you forever.
You're gonna have to adjust
your attitude sooner or later.
Ha!
I never ask you to defend me.
[SHINYA sighs]
You Hiragis control
the Imperial Demon Army.
You don't need a second-class
Ichinose hangin' around.
So, I'm out. I've got
some sleep to catch up on.
[SEISHIRO] Tch. At least you
know your place, dead weight.
We'll handle things like we
always have. Without you.
It's a wonder humanity's
still kicking. Later.
Ugh... Feels like I
lost a few brain-cells.
[YUICHIRO] You can't hide
from me today, Guren!
[YUICHIRO yells]
[GUREN grunts, chuckles]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[GUREN] There's no beating
around the bush with you.
[YUICHIRO yelps]
[grunts]
[GUREN]
It's kinda refreshing
after dealing with
pointless politics all day.
You know what I'm after!
Now, quit wasting my time
and give me a Cursed Gear!
I can handle the demon.
Oh, yeah? This have
anything to do
with getting vengeance
for your family?
Of course! It's the only
thing I've lived for
ever since you brought me here!
We need to get you a date. Soon.
[GUREN] I better pacify this
idiot before he makes a scene.
Last thing I need is him
getting the Hiragis' attention.
[GUREN] Fine. Let's go make
a contract with a demon.
Then, you'll join us
on the front line.
Huh? No joke?
[GUREN]
Sure, why not?
I don't care if you haven't
finished your training.
That way, it's your
fault if you die.
[laughs]
Like we need to worry
about that happening.
I'm a badass! I'll be slaying
monsters from dusk till dawn!
[chuckles]
You really are an idiot, huh?
Oh, and there's one
more thing, Yu.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
[YUICHIRO grunts]
That's for trying to
kick a superior officer!
[YUICHIRO groans]
[GUREN sighs]
The burdens of command
can really take it out of ya.
But, I've gotta admit,
things are getting a lot less
boring around here. Heh.
[SHINOA]
What happened to your head?
Let me guess, you skipped class
and got into another fight?
What's it to you?
You should know Guren doesn't
pull any punches, by now.
Umm. Why'd you ask if you knew?
It's fun. Congrats, by the way.
[YUICHIRO]
Hm?
[SHINOA]
On the demon contract.
He finally approved
it, didn't he?
Yeah. But you know him.
He makes choices on a whim
and doesn't follow through.
You can't fool me.
I can tell you're nearly
bursting at the seams.
No, I'm not!
[SHINOA]
Don't worry about it.
[YUICHIRO]
Hm?
[SHINOA] Lieutenant
Colonel Guren may have
a razor-sharp tongue and a
general fondness for brutality,
but he always
keeps his promises.
Finally. It's happening.
[YUICHIRO] I'll get the power
to kill those parasites.
[FERID]
The time is near.
[FERID] You must be
overjoyed. It won't be long
until you get the chance to
see your precious angel again.
I have such high hopes
for you, Mika.
Hm.
[MIKAELA grunts]
C'mon! Hurry!
[gasps]
[BOY gasps]
It's all right.
[SISTER grunts]
All right. Pay attention!
I've already finished
grading your written exams,
so I'll just be handing those
out and calling it a day, okay?
Remember, this score is crucial
to your overall
Cursed Gear ranking.
The way you perform in class
is just as important
as in training.
I expect those of you with
less than passing grades
to put extra effort into
your studies from now on.
Uh. Uhh...
Huh?
[yelps]
[SHINOA]
Let me see!
Uh-- Give it back!
Oh, wow! Would you
look at this score?
How impressive!
[YUICHIRO]
Hey, Cut it out!
--[SHINOA giggles]
--[YUICHIRO grunts]
[SHINOA]
You've really out done yourself!
They say only super humans
can get a score like this!
[YUICHIRO]
Quit bein' such a pest!
[SHINOA]
Don't you want to share it?
--You should be so very proud!
--[YUICHIRO] Dammit, Shinoa!
--[SHINOA laughs]
--Give that back to me!
--[SHINOA squeaks]
--[YUICHIRO grunts]
[STUDENT A]
How'd he get zero points?
That takes a special
kind of dumb.
Whoa. That's Crazy!
---I thought my handwriting
--[YUICHIRO yells]
--sucked, but this guy
--[yelling]
--takes the cake.
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--[YOICHIRO grunts]
[YUICHIRO]
What's your problem?
Can't you find someone
else to annoy?
Now, is that any way
to talk to a lady?
Especially one who's
trying to help you fit in.
You could try to show
some gratitude.
You can take your gratitude
and choke on it!
I'll tell you what I
keep telling Guren,
I don't need friends to
stick it to the bloodsuckers!
Are we clear?
Yeah, we're as clear as crystal.
Just don't come crying
to me when you realize
that you're completely
worthless by yourself.
Oh, yeah?
I'll kill 50 of those fangs
with my eyes closed.
[SHINOA]
Said the childish fool.
You're a childish fool.
[YOICHI] Come on, it makes
sense that you failed.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Sorry, that didn't come
out like I meant it to.
I'm just saying that,
since you spent several years
as a prisoner of the vampires,
your Japanese reading and
writing skills aren't as strong
as your English and Latin are.
So, it makes sense
that you failed.
Uh... Well, yeah. But that
goes without saying.
[KIMIZUKI] That excuse is
crappier than your test score.
Huh?
[YUICHIRO]
How would you know-- Ah!
[growls]
Then what's your score?
It better be epic,
or I'll pop you one for
being an arrogant ass.
Come on, Four Eyes, let's see
how smart you really are.
See for yourself.
Latin, English, and Japanese
spell-craft. Easy stuff.
Foreign languages aren't
even my strong suit.
I should be no match
for a seasoned
study-abroad poser like you.
[growls]
How 'bout I use you for
vamp killing practice?
Yeah, tough guy?
C'mon let's see ya try!
[BOTH growling]
Yu! Please stop fighting!
--[YUICHIRO growls]
--[KIMIZUKI] Waiting!
Uh... By the way.
I still haven't dismissed
you from class yet.
[YUICHIRO] Open your
stupid mouth one more time!
[KIMIZUKI] I can do the
world a favor and...
Hey! I can hear you morons
half-way down the hall!
What's the deal?
Uh, welcome back,
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
--I hope everything went well.
--[YOICHI] Calm down, you guys!
As well as you'd expect.
What else is new?
Anyway, is there a reason
for all the racket?
Those two...
[GUREN groans]
[YUICHIRO, KIMIZUKI growling]
[GUREN]
I should've known.
Wait. Let's put this
on hold for now.
Guren's come out of hiding.
What's the deal?
I thought you said I was gonna
get to contract with a Demon!
How much longer do I have to--
Let me do the talking.
You're way too loud.
With all due respect. I think
you owe us an explanation.
You have an obligation
to this class, but you left
for over ten days without
any regard for your students.
I think giving us some Cursed
Gear would make up for that.
Really?
You think a bunch of
dumbass losers like you
have what it takes to
tangle with a demon, huh?
--[YUICHIRO] No doubt about it!
--Uh?
The only dumbass in here
is Kimizuki. I won't fail!
Your test score says otherwise.
No one asked for your opinion!
[BOTH grunt]
[YUICHIRO, KIMIZUKI groan]
[GUREN]
So. What's your assessment?
Can this class resist
the demon's temptation?
Hmm... Well, there's always
room for improvement.
But those two are much
stronger than I was at 16.
I think they could do it.
[GUREN]
What about the others?
There are a few contenders.
But, Yoichi Saotome
takes the cake.
He has a surprisingly high
stability against demons.
Really? Okay then.
Why don't we give it a shot now?
It's less complicated that way.
No! You can't do that
in the classroom!
Oh, my! Are you
planning to attack?
This sure got interesting fast.
[GUREN]
Hope you're ready, kids!
If you die from this,
blame yourselves for
not training hard enough!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENTS screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[STUDENT B groans]
Dude. What the hell
is going on?
It feels just like...
my heart's being squeezed!
[gasps]
What's wrong with everyone?
[whimpers]
I think that's enough for now.
[STUDENTS groaning]
[GUREN]
All right. Good.
If you're still conscious,
you've got a chance.
Make no mistake, you've
got a long way to go.
But, if you continue to train
and study your spell-craft,
you could move into the Contract
Ceremony for a Cursed Gear.
The five of you that are
still on your feet.
You just earned
yourself four stars.
You'll get to try out for a
Black Demon Series Cursed Gear;
the same rank of
weapon as my sword.
[BOTH groan]
Well... I guess
there's only three.
Yu... Kimizuki... and Yoichi.
[GUREN]
Hm.
I wish you had passed out.
Ha!
Dealing with demons
is like a day at the
beach for you, isn't it?
Guess I should expect as much
from General Hiragi's daughter.
You probably didn't even
use a ward. What a turn-off.
Aww, don't be that way.
You know I'm the cutest thing
you've ever seen in your life.
--[GUREN] Piss off.
--[SHINOA giggles]
Let's go before I
change my mind.
So, uh...
Lieutenant Colonel Guren,
I know I should expect
unconventional tests
and tactics from you,
but I'm not entirely sure
letting Yoichi try out
for the Black Demon
Series is a good idea.
[GUREN] Do you have a
problem with my decision?
No, sir, that's not what
I'm saying. It's just...
I'm not certain he has enough
strength to accept a demon in--
[GUREN] Tough. If he doesn't
have the strength, he dies.
That's the world we live in.
We're not playing games here.
[gasps]
But, sir...
For crying out loud.
Yoichi, tell me.
You still want to avenge
your sister's death
at the hands of the
vampires, don't you?
[gasps]
Yes, of course.
All right. Are you
willing to die for it?
[grunts]
I dunno.
Then you should quit right now.
If you have any doubts,
go back up those stairs.
[gasps]
--[YUICHIRO] Go, Yoichi.
--[YOICHI gasps]
This isn't the kind of place
a nice guy like you should be,
and you know it.
--I agree, Saotome.
--[YOICHI gasps]
Leave while you can.
[gasps]
[YOICHI] No matter how hard I
cover my ears, I still hear it.
[YOICHI] I'm still under
that bed, frightened.
Did you not hear what
I said? Get outta here!
[YOICHI] I've made up
my mind. I'm doing it.
This is the only way I'll
get the strength I need.
I have to make sure that
nothing in this world
can take away the people
I hold dear ever again!
[YUICHIRO] Damn. In the end,
he's no different than I am.
[GUREN]
Hm.
All right. Let's
keep movin', people.
[GUREN]
Time for the ceremony.
[YOICHI grunts]
[YUICHIRO]
Hey!
Huh?
Getting cold feet now
isn't gonna help.
[YOICHI]
Uh...
[KIMIZUKI] There's no
point worrying about it.
[BOTH gasp]
Deal with it. You've
made your choice.
[SHINOA]
Are you sure you'll be able
to "deal with it," Kimizuki?
You were standing at first.
Then you leaned over. Was the
demon too much to handle?
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
[SHINOA]
You saw it too, right, Yoichi?
Me? Well... Yeah.
Ah.
Stop paying attention
to the small things!
[YUICHIRO] They weren't the
only ones who saw it, Kimizuki.
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
In fact, I remember you
being in a lot of agony.
The last thing you
should be doing
is getting too comfortable, Yu.
The demon you'll make
a contract with
is much stronger
than the last one.
If you let your guard down
for an instant, it'll kill you.
Yeah, I already know.
[YUICHIRO, YOICHI,
KIMIZUKI gasp]
Welcome to the edge of hell.
What is this? A temple?
It's the home of the thing
you want most of all.
The highest-ranking weapons
with Demon Kings sealed
inside them are kept here.
The "highest-ranking," huh?
So. If I have one of these,
I can kill the vampires?
[GUREN] That depends
on your personal skill.
Okay. But they're all the
same as your sword, right?
[GUREN]
Yes.
The rare Black Demon Series.
Quit asking questions.
Let's get started.
I've got more
important things to do
than hang out in a dark cellar
with a group of newbies.
Fine. What do I have to do?
[GUREN] Pick a weapon you like
and enter the spell circle.
Once you touch the weapon,
the Contract Ceremony
will begin automatically.
If you don't lose to the demon,
you'll gain its power.
[KIMIZUKI]
And what if we do lose?
[GUREN] You'll either become
a man-eating monster,
or the demon's power will
crush your soul and kill you.
[chuckles]
Either way, you'll end up dead.
If you start to go monster
on us, I'll kill you myself.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO chuckles]
[YUICHIRO]
Fine by me.
I've been waiting a long time
for a chance like this.
Besides, I'd rather
fight with a demon
than sit through
another boring lecture.
The vampires will suffer.
For Mika and my family,
I'll exterminate every
last one of them.
[YUICHIRO] That's the only
thing I still live for!
Then draw, and it'll begin.
All right, you bastard,
let's dance! Give me your power!
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
"New Family."