[YUICHIRO panting]
[BOTH panting]
It can't be.
Yuichiro?
[GUREN]
What are you waiting for?
[BOTH gasp]
Activate the curse
and kill him! Hurry!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[GUREN]
That's an order!
[gasps]
--[panting]
--[YUICHIRO] I can't.
[GUREN grunts]
You damn rookie!
[MIKAELA grunting]
[YUICHIRO gasping]
The hell?
[GUREN]
What was that?
You had him! Why didn't
you make the kill?
Uh. I think he--
[GUREN groans]
[YUICHIRO]
Guren, are you all right?
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Worry about yourself, idiot! Did
you forget this is a war zone?
Keep your eyes on the enemy!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[MITSUBA]
Hey, moron, what's the deal?
You had that bloodsucker
right where you wanted him!
Did you forget how
to use your Gear?
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
[GUREN groaning]
Well, Yu?
I'm sorry.
But if that's who
I think it is...
[YUICHIRO]
My family's with the vampires.
[MIKAELA gasping]
Tell me! Is it
really you, Mikaela?
[MIKAELA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[YUICHIRO]
It is you.
[ALL gasp]
Mika.
[crying]
I'm... so sorry.
I abandoned you!
No. That's not true.
[FERID] Aww. This might be the
sweetest thing I've ever seen.
And just look at how much
dear Yuichiro has sprouted.
What a fateful and unexpected
reunion for the three of us.
Brings back so many memories.
It's almost enough to
bring tears to my eyes.
So, what's the plan?
Your friend is most likely being
manipulated by these humans.
I'm going to save him.
[FERID] From the hands
of these traitorous dogs?
Yes.
[FERID]
But he's one of them.
Do you really think a
human could befriend us?
I'm sure he'd rather die.
[MIKAELA grunts]
[FERID]
Ah! I know!
I can do for him what
Krul did for you, Mika.
One drop of my blood and
Yuichiro will be reborn.
[MIKAELA grunts]
If you so much as try to lay
a finger on him, I'll kill you.
Oh, come now,
I was only kidding.
You really need to learn
to take a joke, my dear boy.
Now, why don't I help
you rescue your princess?
I'll deal with
the other livestock
while you rescue Yuichiro.
Just leave it to me.
All you need to worry about is
getting him out of harm's way.
[MIKAELA] I'm not surprised
you've made new friends.
You've always been
such a kind soul.
But sometimes you
can be too nice.
So much so, that people
take advantage of you.
[MIKAELA] The truth is,
these friends you've made
are faking it.
They're greedy and
deceitful. All of them.
[FERID chuckles]
Very well. It's been decided.
All of the humans will die,
except for the long
lost lamb, Yuichiro.
[CROWLEY] Looks like I
got here just in time.
[FERID grunts]
Sorry I'm running late,
Third Progenitor.
[FERID]
Ah, Crowley!
So glad you could
make it to the party.
Him again.
I took a little detour
on the way over here.
Of course. Was anything
interesting going on?
[CROWLEY grunts]
Well, now that you're here,
the game I had planned
won't be quite as much fun.
But, we could play a new one.
It's called "Take them alive."
We'll capture the
Moon Demon Company
and make them our livestock.
I could get behind that.
Damn. We were in trouble
before this guy showed up.
I've got no choice.
[GUREN groans]
Everyone! Prepare to retreat!
[BOTH gasping]
No, we can't just
run away, dammit!
Mika's my family!
I won't leave him
with these monsters!
Shut up. You're willing to let
your comrades die for a vampire?
[YOICHI]
Yu!
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
Let's go.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Please, Yu.
[GUREN]
Fall back!
Keep your formation and retreat
to the second defense line!
[FERID laughs]
[ALL gasp]
Come on, don't you wanna play?
[GUREN]
Break formation!
Damn you!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[YUICHIRO yelling]
What the hell's
gotten into you?
Die! You bastard!
[yelling]
[YUICHIRO grunting]
Stop, Yu!
What is that idiot thinking?
No, wait!
[YUICHIRO grunting]
You are fast, but you've
still got a lot to learn.
[FERID gasps]
[GUREN growls]
--[YUICHIRO yelps]
--[GUREN grunts]
[GUREN gasps]
And you should know by now
that the injured lion's strike
is never quite as sharp!
[GUREN grunts]
Lieutenant Colonel!
[SAYURI grunting]
[LACUS]
Huh?
Move.
--[LACUS grunts]
--[SAYURI yelps]
Why the hurry?
Oh, wow. Still standing?
Looks like we've got
ourselves a hero.
Are you okay?
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
These bastards don't
have any intention
of letting us get to Guren.
In that case, we'll just
have to kill all of them.
Easier said than
done, I'm afraid.
That's why we're having all
this trouble in the first place.
Huh?
The only way out of here
is as livestock or corpses,
so what's it going to be?
[grunts]
Well, we're waiting.
--[SHINOA grunts]
--[VAMPIRE yelps]
[MITSUBA yelling]
[YOICHI grunts]
[YOICHI grunting]
[gasps]
Focus!
[KIMIZUKI grunting]
What are you doing?
Get on your feet!
Yeah. Sorry.
[CROWLEY]
Well, hello. So we meet again.
[KIMIZUKI gasps]
This time, I'm not letting
you get away from me.
[yelps]
[GUREN groaning]
Guren!
[yells]
[gasps]
Watch out!
I've waited so long to
get a taste of your--
[FERID] You see? This is what
I meant about taking a joke.
Be sure to call me
if you need a hand.
[YUICHIRO]
Mika.
[YUICHIRO yelping]
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Let's go. Leave everything
behind and escape with me.
Huh? What do you
mean escape? Answer me.
Why're you with the vampire
who killed our family?
[MIKAELA]
Nevermind that!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Yu!
[gasps]
Don't take your
eyes off the enemy.
[SHINOA grunts]
[YUICHIRO] Hey, let go
of me! Stop playing, Mika!
Tell me what's going on.
You at least owe me that much!
The short version is that
you shouldn't be here!
Not with the humans.
They're just using you.
[YUICHIRO] What? That's the
dumbest thing I've ever heard!
Shut up and put me down!
[YUICHIRO]
The humans are using me?
What're you saying?
Aren't you still a...?
[grunts]
Wait. You are human, right?
Don't tell me that
they changed you.
[gasps] Is this because of me?
Is this because I abandoned you?
No! You didn't do
anything wrong!
Then why, Mika?
[MIKAELA] Let's just go.
It isn't safe here.
Please, Yu. Come with me.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
No. I'm staying until it's over.
It's just... they're
friends. I can't leave.
You're wrong! They only
see you as a tool!
Please, Yu! Trust me!
I'm trying to save you
before it's too late!
[explosion]
[YOICHI]
Shinoa!
[gasps]
[SHINOA groaning]
Shinoa!
[grunts]
Please. Don't look back.
There's nothing behind you.
Nothing important.
Just come with me!
[yelps]
[gasps]
Let go of her!
[KIMIZUKI grunting]
Come on!
[MITSUBA yelps]
They're in trouble!
There's nothing you
can do to help them!
Get off me!
[BOTH grunting]
You can't! Just
forget about them.
In the end, they'll betray
you and toss you aside!
[MITSUBA screaming]
Mitsuba!
Let's get out of here
before they capture you!
[YOICHI gasping]
I won't run away again!
[MIKAELA yelps]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[SHINOA groaning]
Go, Yu. Run!
[SHINOA grunts]
Hush. Livestock don't speak.
Please, call them
off! Hurry, Mika!
You should be worried
about yourself.
It's too late for them now.
[SHINOA whimpering]
[CROWLING slurping]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[YUICHIRO screaming]
[crying]
Yu? What's the matter?
[gasps]
Talk to me, Asuramaru.
[ASURAMARU]
Hm? About what?
What's happening to me?
You're not trying to
possess me, are you?
No. This has nothing
to do with me.
It seems we've got a
big problem on our hands.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
I've been around for a while,
but I never thought
I'd be terrified
of a monster inside the
human I was possessing.
There. You see how the
clouds are parting?
It's as if the
heavens have opened
to shine judgment
on this cursed world.
You know, I think
your friend is right.
Listen to him and
escape while you can.
This might be your
one and only chance.
[ASURAMARU] If you stay here,
you won't be human for long.
[gasps]
Wait. What?
--[horn blowing]
--[gasps]
[horns blowing]
[ASURAMARU]
I'm afraid it's too late.
The non-human part of you
is about to lose all control.
[YUICHIRO yelping]
[YUICHIRO screaming]
[GUREN groaning]
And so it begins.
[SHINOA whimpering]
[YUICHIRO screaming]
It's true. The humans have
been using him all along.
Snap out of it! Please, Yu!
Leave this place with me!
[MIKAELA grunting]
[CROWLEY]
Huh?
[whimpering]
[CROWLEY] I don't know what that
is, but it doesn't look good.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[CROWLEY whistles]
That' a lotta damage.
Very impressive.
[CROWLEY grunting]
[CROWLEY grunts]
--[YUICHIRO growls]
--[CROWLEY yelps]
[CROWLEY grunting]
No, Yu! Stop!
[sighs]
You went and got my
clothes all dirty.
[CROWLEY grunting]
[gasps]
[SHINOA yelps]
[SHINOA gasps]
[CROWLEY]
That's one creepy monster.
Seriously, it's so revolting
I've completely
lost my appetite.
[GUREN groaning]
[CROWLEY]
What is that thing, Ferid?
[FERID]
Hm.
I don't know. Do you?
Nah. We'll just
have to wait 'n see.
Let me guess,
this is the result of human
experimentation, isn't it?
Tell me,
where does that infinite
greed of yours come from?
[YUICHIRO groanss]
[yelps]
[GUREN groaning]
[FERID]
Honestly, it scares me.
Besides, you always seem
to be losing control of it.
See?
[YUICHIRO groans]
Sinners. Sinners must die.
Sinners must all be annihilated.
[SHINOA whimpers]
No.
[GUREN]
Shinoa!
[SHINOA grunts]
You're the only one
who can help him!
There's still a chance
that he can come back!
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO roars]
--[YUICHIRO growls]
--[SHINOA yelps]
[SHINOA yelps]
[gasps]
[metal clangs]
[MIKAELA groaning]
No, Yu. Don't do it!
You'd never be able
to forgive yourself!
Why? Why did you... save me?
[MIKAELA]
Shut up, human.
This is happening
because you used him!
[MIKAELA grunts]
[MIKAELA]
Damn it. My injury won't heal.
[YUICHIRO]
Annihilate... every sinner!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
--[MIKAELA groaning]
--[SHINOA whimpering]
[GUREN]
Shinoa!
[SHINOA gasps]
What're you waiting for?
Our lives depend on you! Go!
[SHINOA grunts]
[SHINOA yells]
Yu! Stop it!
Please, you have to!
Or all of us are going to die!
Don't you dare touch him!
Get your filthy
hands off my family!
Stop it!
[YUICHIRO screaming]
[MIKAELA grunts]
--[YUICHIRO groaning]
--[SHINOA whimpering]
Please, Yu! Don't do it!
[YUICHIRO yelling]
Come back to us!
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[thud]
[SHINOA]
Yu! I'm right here.
[SHINOA crying]
You're okay.
Damn you humans
and your treachery.
[grunts]
You'll pay for this.
[GUREN chuckles]
So, how do ya like
my trump card?
For a rookie, he puts
on one hell of a show.
Sadly, for you, he didn't
really achieve anything.
I wouldn't be so sure.
He's managed to distract you.
And that was our main
objective all along.
[FERID gasps]
Uh-oh. They've seen us.
But not soon enough
to make a difference.
Destroy our enemies, Byakkomaru.
[SHINYA] Oh, and try not
to hit Guren, okay?
Boom.
[roaring]
[FERID] Whew. That was
too close for comfort.
If it hadn't been
for his big mouth,
I'd be a smoking pile
of ash right now. Uh.
It appears we're surrounded.
[grunts]
[KURETO]
Not bad, Lieutenant Colonel.
I suppose junior branch
garbage has its use.
You're done here. The Hiragi
family will be taking over.
All right, men! I want
those nobles taken alive!
[KURETO] We need to show
them, once and for all,
what happens to anyone or
anything that opposes humanity,
the Japanese
Imperial Demon Army,
or the might of
the Hiragi family.
Here we go.
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
"Everyone's a Sinner."