[MIKAELA]
Hello again, Yu.
Are you ever going
to tell me why
you abandoned your own family?
Aw, c'mon, say it.
If you don't, you're gonna
keep having this dream.
It's a reflection of the
darkness inside of you.
I now dwell within you.
And I am...
[ASURAMARU]
I am your power.
Call for me when you feel
like your spirit's breaking.
You must surrender
yourself to me.
Then I can get you the
revenge that you so desire.
Oh! And there's one last thing.
Wake up, Yu.
[alarm rings]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[yawns]
Heh.
[YUICHIRO]
Finally.
It's about time I got the
chance to kill some vampires.
[YUICHIRO]
Mika...
[footsteps clacking]
[SHINOA]
My, my, take a look at you!
That uniform looks
awfully good on ya.
Oh, thanks. And you...
--[SHINOA] Hm? Hmmm?
--[YUICHIRO grunts]
Oh, never mind.
You don't have to say it.
I know what you're thinking.
"You look drop-dead
gorgeous, Shinoa!"
So... I thought we
were meeting there.
Don't cha want your orders?
Let's hear 'em.
Do you remember the
vampires Guren mentioned?
He wants us to go to
Shinjuku to investigate.
[gasps]
[SHINOA, YUICHIRO gasp]
[train screeches]
Then, let me ask you this.
Are we gonna kill bloodsuckers
when we get there?
We get it. You hate vampires.
Enough with the bloodlust.
Is that all you're
interested in?
There's more to our job
than just killing vampires.
Hey! Are you listening?
But you're so boring.
I guess you don't wanna survive
once we get outside the wall.
[YUICHIRO]
Hmph.
[train screeches]
We're from the
Moon Demon Company.
We have orders beyond the wall.
Would you please let us out?
What? There's no way.
That's an elite squad, right?
Yeah, it's no place
for little kids.
[GUARD 7B]
Shut up! They can hear you.
Hey, he just called you
a kid. How'd ya like that?
They're talking about you
'cause you're so short.
Whatever, I won't
be short forever,
I'm still blossoming.
My sister Mahiru was taller,
and she had the kind of rack
that made all the
boys lust after her.
Huh. I didn't know
you have a sister.
No, I had a sister.
Shinoa, I'm sorry.
What?
You don't have a silly
comeback for that one?
'Kay. Let's get going, Yu.
[SHINOA] In a completely
devastated world like this...
It seems everybody's
lost someone
who's important to them.
It's just a way of life.
[MITSUBA]
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
What in the hell is going on?
You wanna explain why
I've been placed
in a squad full of new recruits?
That girl. Who is she?
Don't know.
Maybe she's a
new member like you!
Let's find out!
Hey! Wait up!
[YOICHI]
There you are.
--Hey, Yu!
--[YUICHIRO] Hey.
Would it kill ya to be on time?
[YUICHIRO] If I have to
look at your ugly mug.
What's goin' on over there?
I could understand if you
had made me team leader
in charge of the newbs,
but you chose her!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Do you seriously
think Shinoa Hiragi
is more qualified than I am?
Well, well. Look who's here.
You! How dare you, Shinoa!
You're no team leader!
Sorry, Mitsu,
but Guren thinks I'm
right for the job.
[grunts]
[GUREN] Don't even think
about it, Mitsuba!
From this day forward, Shinoa
is your team leader, so I--
Don't worry, Lieutenant Colonel,
I can handle Mitsu's temper.
After all, I'm a mature woman.
The whining of an incompetent
loser doesn't affect me one bit.
[growls]
I'll destroy you!
[laughs]
[sighs]
[SHINOA, MITSUBA gasp]
I hope that you ladies
like solitary confinement.
'Cause that's where you're
headed if you keep this up.
I'll behave.
Yeah, I will, too.
[KIMIZUKI, YOICHI,
YOICHIRO gasp]
[GUREN] I'm gonna take
a different route to Shinjuku,
but I'll meet you there.
Before I go, let me
make one thing clear.
The Moon Demon
Company's squads move
in a five-man formation.
That's why Mitsuba's here.
We've found that five
is the golden number
when facing armed vampires.
Any more than that, and
attacks can get confusing.
Any less and we
start losing troops.
So I want the five of you
to stick together.
I don't want any
more in-fighting
or one of you idiots trying
to fly solo. Is that clear?
As crystal, sir! Hear that,
Mr. Reckless Behavior?
Hmph. I can't promise anything.
If I come face-to-face
with a vamp,
I may just have to--
What's your problem?
Oh, wow. Quick reflexes kid.
Now I get it,
Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
[MITSUBA]
You put me on this squad
so I could train the new
recruits. Consider it done, sir!
What're they gonna learn
from a troublemaker?
[MITSUBA] Since when have I
ever caused you any trouble?
Aw, man.
That girl is a pain
in the ass. For real.
Oh, wow.
If you're calling someone
a pain in the ass,
they must be pretty bad.
You say somethin'?
[laughs] Nope, not me! Nuh-uh.
Did her kick hurt?
Kinda. I'm okay.
[GUREN]
Listen up!
Your fellow squad members are
now your comrades, got it?
That means they're more
important than family.
Protect them with your life.
[yawns]
Tch.
Okay.
Are you ready for
your first mission?
[GUREN] I want the five
of you to head to Harajuku.
According to our intel,
there's a growing
vampire settlement there.
Crush them and free the
people they're holding hostage.
Then head north to Shinjuku.
This place is a wreck.
I barely remember what it
used to look like anymore.
I haven't been outside the wall
since I've been in the
Demon Army's custody.
Before you and Kimizuki joined
our general ed class,
you used to patrol
the outside as guards,
didn't you?
That's right. It sucked.
[MITSUBA]
Ha!
You think you're tough
just because you killed
a couple of
Four Horsemen of Johns
right outside the
spell-protected wall?
Anybody could do that, loser.
The ones near the wall
are weak, but once you get
a half mile out or more,
they're ruthless.
They're much stronger
than anything you ever
fought back at headquarters.
You better be ready for
the fight of your lives.
If you're not, then leave now!
We can't afford to have
any weaklings in our squad,
you hear me?
One little slip and we're
all dead, so stay alert!
No chit-chatting,
and don't break formation!
Ugh, amateurs.
She always like this?
[giggles] Could she
be any more adorable?
Seems she's feeling the
pressure of responsibility.
She doesn't want you
dying on her watch.
[YOICHI grunts]
Oh... It's Harajuku station!
Well, this is the spot.
Yeah. Now how're we supposed
to find the vampires?
--[GIRL 7A screams]
--[ALL gasp]
[GIRL 7A panting]
[YUICHIRO gasps]
A Four Horsemen of John!
Dammit!
What do you think you're doing?
Helping!
Don't break formation!
[panting] Someone help!
[GIRL 7A yelps]
We gotta go and save her!
C'mon! That monster's
gonna kill her!
[MITSUBA]
Shut up!
[YUICHIRO] What good's the
Vampire Extermination Unit
if we can't even save one kid?
Shut up!
Let go of me!
Can't you see this is
one of their traps?
As soon as we go
out to save her,
they'll attack and
we'll all be dead!
[GIRL 7A gasps]
[rumbling]
[gasps, whimpers]
[YUICHIRO] I'm willing to
put my life on the line.
Let me save her!
Forget it! We're gonna standby!
Are you really gonna
let that little girl die?
If you wanna standby,
then so be it,
but I'm not abandoning
anyone ever again!
[gasps]
[MITSUBA]
Wait!
Oh no.
[SHINOA]
Don't move, Kimizuki.
The vampires are coming.
We have to be on alert.
[gasps, yelps]
[GIRL 7A whimpering]
[gasps]
[GIRL 7A]
No!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
The vampires are
using her as bait
to lure us out.
Are you sure?
'Cause that doesn't make sense.
The Four Horsemen of John
have no will of their own.
So why would they
obey the vampires?
[SHINOA] They're not obeying,
they only kill humans.
They're simply following
their natural instincts.
It's as if they were
created to keep
humanity's population
under control.
Go, now!
[gasps]
You're dead!
[gasps] Here come the vamps!
[MITSUBA]
See? I told ya!
They release bait
for the monsters,
and then attack the
humans who try to help.
Huh.
That was too easy.
[MITSUBA] It's the oldest
vampire trick in the book!
Heads up, kid!
[YUICHIRO, VAMPIRES grunting]
[grunting]
[VAMPIRE 7B yells]
[YUICHIRO]
Lend me your power.
[VAMPIRE 7C grunts]
[YUICHIRO]
Asuramaru!
So strong. Who's he?
[MITSUBA]
Hyakuya!
[gasps]
You left yourself
wide open, dumbass.
Oh, wow. Thanks, guys.
You saved me.
--[MITSUBA grunts]
--[YUICHIRO gasps]
[VAMPIRE 7C]
How do they have Cursed Gear?
They're the Vampire
Extermination Unit.
Call for backup. I'll bet
we can capture them.
[YUICHIRO]
No way! Hya!
[ASURAMARU roars]
[grunts]
All right, that's enough. Now.
I think we should retreat.
Ha. Go right ahead.
Run from the butcher, livestock.
[YUICHIRO]
What the hell did you call us?
[grunts]
[VAMPIRE 7B]
Let's fall back!
Ain't gonna happen!
[SHINOA] Let 'em go, Yu!
We're behind enemy lines.
We need to leave before
their backup gets here.
Okay, fine.
[slap]
[MITSUBA]
How could you be so stupid?
Your reckless behavior put
our entire squad in danger!
You're lucky those
vampires only had
second class weapons!
Otherwise, we'd be--
Look, I'm sorry.
I should've followed orders.
But I don't regret what I did.
That girl would've been
dead if it wasn't for me.
Go ahead. Punch me
as much as you want,
if it'll make you feel better.
But I would do it
all over again.
You're an idiot.
I hate people like you
more than anything.
You're impulsive and stubborn.
You would put your
whole squad in danger.
[GIRL 7A]
Excuse me.
Thanks for saving me.
Hey, don't mention it.
I was just doing
my job, that's all.
[GIRL 7A]
Huh?
Don't worry. You're
in good hands now.
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army
is going to keep you safe.
Okay!
[MITSUBA] Just so you know.
I hate your guts!
[YUICHIRO]
Huh...?
[MITSUBA]
Hmph!
[SHINOA]
Don't let her get to you.
Everyone in Moon Demon Company
has a bit of a troubled past.
And our friend Mitsuba
is no exception.
Hold up. What does that mean?
Like I would tell you!
[MITSUBA] What's with that
Yuichiro Hyakuya guy?
Ignoring orders and flying solo?
I can't believe the
Lieutenant Colonel
was dumb enough to let that punk
into the Moon Demon Company!
[SHINOA] Hmph! At first,
they were like two rams,
butting heads.
But it wasn't long before
they started to fall in love.
With him?! No way!
[SHINOA] Do you really
hate him that much?
[MITSUBA]
Of course I do.
I hate anyone who would
put their comrades at risk.
[SHINOA] He upsets you
because he reminds you
of yourself back in
the day. Doesn't he?
Stay here!
How many times have I told
you not to break formation?
I don't give a crap
about formation.
Our comrade's about to die!
[yells]
I did it!
[gasps]
You idiot. [coughs]
What did I do?
[TROOPER 7A]
Hurry. Get outta here!
[gasping, whimpering]
[SHINOA]
It wasn't your fault.
You did everything you
could in your situation.
What happened that day had
nothing to do with you
--breaking formation, Mitsu.
--[thud]
[MITSUBA]
Shinoa.
[SHINOA]
Yeah?
Don't ever come in while
I'm showering again.
[giggles] Aw, c'mon,
don't be so shy!
Wha...? No!
--[SHINOA giggling]
--[MITSUBA yelling]
I can't tell if they're
giggling or fighting.
[laughs]
[gasps]
If you don't mind,
there's something important
that I'd like to ask
you about. Cool?
We wanna save other people.
Do the vampires have a lair?
And if so, where can we find it?
[YUICHIRO]
It's okay.
You don't have to tell us
anything if you don't want to.
We understand.
[SHINOA]
Goodness! I feel so refreshed!
Yeah, I bet you do, perv!
[SHINOA, MITSUBA]
Huh?
--[gasps]
--[YOICHI] Um...
I don't mind telling.
I wanna show my appreciation.
[YUICHIRO] Don't worry
about that. It's not a big deal.
You must be scared, and I
don't blame you one bit.
You don't have to tell us
just 'cause we saved you.
--[MITSUBA] Dumbass.
--[YUICHIRO] Wha...?
It's Omotesando.
[grunts]
That's where you'll
find the vampire's lair.
According to the girl,
the vampires have a lair in
the Omotesando subway station.
She said they're actually
raising human children there.
[KIMIZUKI]
Question.
[SHINOA]
Yes? What is it, Kimizuki?
[KIMIZUKI] What are we going
to do about the civilians
they've captured?
We'll ignore them for now.
They're not our priority
on this mission.
We've got bigger things
to worry about.
What's that look for?
If you've got a problem,
you can go back to Shibuya.
[YUICHIRO]
Nope, no problems here.
As long as I get to kill
bloodsuckers, I'm good.
[SHINOA]
Okay, everyone, stay alert!
Also, if the vampires are awake
and armed when we go in,
we'll have to retreat.
[gasps] We're gonna
retreat again?!
This is it.
To be honest, you guys
might be able to fend off
the vampires on your own
since you have the
Black Demon Series.
But that's dangerous,
so I think it'd be best
for us to stick together.
Be careful.
And whatever you do,
don't break formati--
Yeah, yeah, I won't.
At least you recognize
I could do it alone.
That's enough for me.
[SHINOA]
All right, team. Let's move out.
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End.
"First Extermination."