This is it.
To be honest, you guys
might be able to fend off
the vampires on your own
since you have the
Black Demon Series.
But that's dangerous,
so I think it'd be best
for us to stick together.
Be careful.
And whatever you do,
don't break forma--
Yeah, yeah, I won't.
At least you recognize
I could do it alone.
That's enough for me.
[SHINOA]
All right, team. Let's move out.
The little girl we rescued said
that there are seven
vampires down here.
With any luck, they're
sleeping right now
and we can take
them by surprise.
Whatever the case,
we do this by the book.
It's important that
we stay in formation
and watch each other's backs.
Don't get separated.
And don't act alone.
What is this?
[YUICHIRO]
They're dressed like livestock.
[MITSUBA]
Let's keep moving.
We're going straight to B3.
That's the floor the
vampires should be on.
[grunts]
If no one's guarding them,
then why don't the
captives escape?
[MITSUBA] Because it's crawling
with monsters outside.
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
[SHINOA] The vampires
promised to protect them
as the lesser of two evils.
[KIMIZUKI] And in return,
they offer up their blood?
Those bloodsuckers won't get
another drop from them.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Form Up! Prepare
to attack! Draw!
Don't let him call for backup.
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[YUICHIRO yells]
[wretches] Livestock...
You'll pay for this.
How does it feel to be
killed by your food,
you bastard? Burn in hell!
[VAMPIRE 8A groans]
One down.
Damn you. Yuichiro!
How many times have I
told you not to jump ahead
and act on your own?
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO]
I followed your rules.
I assessed the enemy, and didn't
draw until you said to.
You need to stop complaining
and give me some credit.
[MITSUBA grunts]
[VAMPIRE 8C, YUICHIRO grunt]
[gasps]
[VAMPIRE 8C groans]
[laughs] Not fast enough!
I've waited four
years to do this.
Now you're gonna pay!
You imbecile.
Just because you
blocked me once doesn't--
Whoa. Where's this
power coming from?
[SHINOA]
That was amazing!
I figured he had to be good
since the Lieutenant Colonel
has taken such an
interest in his training,
but I didn't know
he was this strong.
Yeah, you wasted that vamp!
You're almost as good
as I am, chump.
Almost? Let's test that.
Just you and me, one on one.
You couldn't handle it.
If we were to fight,
you'd be dead
before you could even
get your sword out.
--Bring it on, Four Eyes.
--[KIMIZUKI] Call me that
--[YOICHI] Whoa, guys.
--one more time. I dare you.
--[YUICHIRO] Four Eyes!
--[MITSUBA] Stupid boys.
[SHINOA giggles] They're the
Lieutenant Colonel's favorites.
A couple-a troublemakers
who're bad at teamwork.
I bet he put you on this squad
so you can whip the boys
into shape and make
them better soldiers.
[grunts]
That's enough messing around!
We've still got five
more targets left.
[footsteps clacking]
They've come to us.
[MITSUBA]
Get ready.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[grunts]
Mitsuba!
Eight of 'em!
[MITSUBA]
You're not supposed to be here.
Our intelligence was solid.
Your intelligence? Ha, ha!
And just where do you think
that information came from?
Thanks for saving me.
I'll tell you.
You used her. An
innocent little girl!
[VAMPIRE 8B laughs]
Human beings are so disgusting.
Threaten to drain the
blood from the people
they care about most,
and they'll do anything
you ask of them.
[MITSUBA] Don't attack!
I'm as good as dead now.
Retreat!
[YUICHIRO] Why do I keep
having to repeat myself?
There's no way I'm ever
leaving a comrade behind!
I'm sorry. But I
have to disobey!
[YUICHIRO, VAMPIRES grunting]
[VAMPIRE 8D grunts]
[yelps]
[VAMPIRE 7A, KIMIZUKI grunting]
Go!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
No. Stop it!
[YUICHIRO groans]
Save yourselves.
Please, don't. Not again.
[YUICHIRO grunts]
Damn livestock.
[yells]
He saved her!
[YUICHIRO]
What was it you said
about humans being disgusting?
That we're scum who'll
turn on one another
if you threaten our
friends and family?
That we don't have
a sense of pride?
I guess you know us pretty well.
What you said is true.
Humans will do anything for
the people we care about.
We'll push ourselves
to the brink,
make contracts with demons,
and become devils ourselves.
You might think
that's repulsive.
But I would call it honorable.
The disgusting one is you!
[VAMPIRES gasp]
Wow. You really know
how to rile 'em up.
[laughs]
Right. Let's do this.
We can take these guys.
Absolutely. From what
I can tell,
all of them are armed
with second-class weapons.
But there are still
a few more of them than us.
We were outnumbered
from the start.
What do ya say?
Strike hard.
Don't let a single
one of them escape.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thank you!
[GIRL 8A]
Huh?
You're safe!
Sir, please forgive me!
They... I didn't... Sorry!
You were trying to protect
the people you
care about. I get that.
I put you in danger!
You were doing what
you thought was right.
No need to apologize.
[gasps]
[SHINOA] After being rescued
from a dangerous situation,
the girl watches her
knight in shining armor.
Passion fills the air.
These two are destined
to fall in love!
Not gonna happen!
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you know what Yu's story is?
I mean, why does he fight?
He grew up in captivity.
He and his friends made
an attempt to escape.
[SHINOA]
But it didn't work out.
Huh?
Shinoa told me about
what happened to you.
Is it true? Did you leave
your friends behind
when they were attacked?
[gasps] That's none
of your damned business.
Don't poke around in my past.
[MITSUBA]
Wait!
You were right to.
I know that this probably
doesn't mean anything
coming from me, but still.
I don't think you
did anything wrong.
I'm glad you survived.
[YUICHIRO] I left my family
behind to save my own skin.
Even though they were dying.
I should've stayed
with them until the end.
I can't change what happened.
That's why I will never...
Just, forget it.
[MITSUBA]
Yu!
[YUICHIRO]
What? I've said everything I...
Um, earlier...
he had me. I wanna say.
[YUICHIRO]
Hm?
Uh... Ugh!
Wait, you wanna say what?
[MITSUBA]
Just that you almost
got us all killed
today, you idiot!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
That's what this is about?
[KIMIZUKI] Hey, are you two
lovebirds done flirting yet?
We're ready to go.
[MITSUBA]
What? Ugh! You shut up!
[YUICHIRO] Whoa! You've
gotta be kidding me.
You really know how
to hotwire a car?
Yup.
Well, this is perfect!
We finally found something
you're good at!
Would you shut up?
But seriously.
The only time I've
ridden in a car
was when I was a little kid.
I almost forgot about 'em.
There weren't any
in the vampire's city.
Plus, gas is so rare nowadays,
that you hardly ever
see them around Shibuya.
[engine revs]
[YUICHIRO laughs] Hell yeah!
You did it! Let's ride!
Hey, Kimizuki. Uh...
When's it gonna be my turn
to drive this thing?
Never.
You've got no experience
behind the wheel.
Well, not technically.
But I am a quick learner!
Just don't touch
anything for now.
I'll give you an intro
lesson or something later.
[gasps] You mean you can
hotwire and drive a car?
I guess you are cool!
You're like the
annoying little brother
I never wanted.
These actually aren't that bad.
[KIMIZUKI] I got it started.
No thanks to any of you.
[YOICHI]
Impressive!
So where'd you learn
how to do that?
You do know that it's
a crime to steal a car,
right Kimizuki?
Whatever. Let's just
get on the road.
[ALL gasp]
Crap! That wasn't right.
Then it must be this way.
[KIMIZUKI]
What do you think you're--?!
I'm gonna kill you!
Hey, hop in!
I think I've got this
driving thing figured out.
[KIMIZUKI]
You're so dead!
Don't you ever try that again!
[YUICHIRO]
I had a rough start!
[KIMIZUKI]
You almost killed me!
--[MITSUBA] Jeez.
--[YUICHIRO] Yeah, but I didn't.
[MITSUBA] Are those two
ever gonna stop fighting?
[YOICHI laughs nervously]
Probably not. Well,
it looks as if my
expert driving skills
are required once again.
Wait, you're gonna drive?
Get in! Next stop, Shinjuku.
Uh-oh. Um...
[YUICHIRO, KIMIZUKI laugh]
She can't even see
over the steering wheel.
Shinoa, you're way too short!
[KIMIZUKI, YUICHIRO laughing]
A-ha... You think so, huh?
You know, we probably shouldn't
make fun of Shinoa's
height anymore.
[KIMIZUKI] I actually
agree with you for once.
[explosions]
[YUICHIRO]
What's that?
[KIMIZUKI]
Maybe a Four Horsemen of John?
Should we go kill it?
No. If we kill one,
then more will just show up.
Let's head to Shinjuku and
see if we can lose them.
Not good.
That banging sound. We're
headed straight for it.
[YOICHI gasps]
All right. Everyone
stay on alert.
We have no idea who or what
might be waiting for us here.
Shinjuku is just ahead.
We should be able to see
the defensive barrier soon.
[ALL gasp]
What the...?
[explosion]
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[YUICHIRO]
No, don't slow down!
Hit him! That guy's a noble!
[grunts]
[YUICHIRO, SHINOA yelp]
Eat this!
My sword. Gain power
from my blood.
No way!
Yoichi!
That was somethin'! He's strong!
Listen up! Stay in formation.
He is wielding a
first-class weapon!
No one attacks him alone.
[CROWLEY grunts, chuckles]
Hey. You're pretty
good for a human.
Who are you exactly?
You guys okay?
Shinoa?
Fine.
[SHINOA] Yuichiro and
Kimizuki should take point
since they're the strongest
one-on-one fighters.
The rest of us will
cover them and tag in
if things start to look rough.
We can't underestimate
this guy's abilities.
This is bad.
[SHINOA] Things just took
a turn for the worse.
What now? Do we retreat?
Getting out of here
would be the best idea.
But I doubt these three
will let us do that.
So we fight at full power.
We let the demons almost
completely possess us.
But that still might
not be enough.
We might not survive.
But we are soldiers.
We knew that from the start.
Okay, fine. If that's
how it's gonna be...
Just know that I'm not
gonna let any of you die.
That's the whole reason
I fought for so much power.
Right, Asuramaru?
Um, Lord Crowley.
What are you doing wasting
your time with these humans?
The Seventh Progenitor
is waiting
for you at the front line.
[CROWLEY]
Hm? Ferid wants to see me?
I probably shouldn't
keep him waiting.
Pity, things were just starting
to get interesting here.
[CROWLEY laughs]
Very well,
I suppose this can
wait until later.
I'll let all of you
go for today.
But next time we meet,
I'm draining every last drop
of your blood.
What?
So long for now, my cute
little blood-bag.
[pants] We're... okay.
We don't have to fight.
[YUICHIRO] That arrogant jerk.
What a bastard!
Treating us as if we
were his playthings.
Pull yourself together.
We need to get
out of here before
they start having
second thoughts.
Let's meet up with
the Shinjuku Units.
Dammit! This is all wrong!
I've got a Cursed Gear.
I'm supposed to be
as strong as he is.
Well, since you've got
the Black Demon Series,
you could always
learn some curses.
That'd help you get
closer to his power level.
Then why haven't you
taught me any?
Well, I could.
But what good is it
if you're the only one
who can defeat a
powerful vampire?
I'd probably be killed
while you fought.
Yoichi. Mitsuba. They'd just
end up dying, too.
That's why we have
to work together.
All of us have to keep training
so that we fight
as a unit of equals.
We're improving.
I was happy to hear you
ask about retreating.
And there's something
else I have to say.
Thank you for saving
my life earlier, Yu.
It's like Lieutenant
Colonel Guren said,
you care about your friends.
Huh? Oh, It was nothing.
[MISTUBA]
Hm.
[rumbling]
You know.
I'm kinda ready to go
back to Shibuya.
I hear ya, but right now
it's not an option.
If Shinjuku falls,
then Shibuya's next.
Your sister's there.
Remember that when we fight.
Let's get moving.
We won't lose Shinjuku.
[YUICHIRO]
Right.
Next time, on Seraph of the End.
"Vampire Attack."