Fire!
[COMMANDER 9A]
Unit Two. Fire!
Good. Stay primed.
The fourth wave is coming.
Enemy aircraft have
already infiltrated
the Southwest region.
If they manage
to break through here,
too, Shinjuku is lost.
But we're not gonna
let them do that!
They've underestimated our will.
No one gets past us.
[gasps]
Here I come!
[OFFICERS screaming]
[OFFICERS yelling]
Oh, wow, am I good or what?
This wall is trashed.
You shouldn't act
so cocky, Lacus.
You were ten feet to
the right of the target.
And yet, all the
livestock are still dead.
We've been hit!
[TROOPER 9B]
What? Where?
[TROOPER 9C]
The Western Wall!
[TROOPER 9A]
Shinjuku is the Demon Army's
second biggest city!
How could we let the
vampires past our defenses?
[TROOPER 9B] Where are the
Vampire Extermination Units?
What's going on?
Didn't you hear what they said?
The vampires are attacking--
[ALL gasp]
[OFFICERS gasp]
[YUICHIRO, SHINOA gasp, grunt]
[ALL grunting]
[KIMIZUKI] Holy Shit. This place
has turned into a warzone.
The Lieutenant Colonel
warned us about this.
Vampires from the Kansai Region
are trying to annihilate
our military operations.
[gasps]
[TROOPER 9A]
Fire!
[gasps] Are those Cursed Gear
the same as my bow?
No. They're not
nearly as powerful.
They're simplified
versions of your weapons.
They're called
Enchanted Gear instead.
Look!
[KIMIZUKI]
Move!
[YUICHIRO, SHINOA grunt]
[CORPORAL NAGAI]
Incoming! Prepare for battle!
[OFFICERS yell]
C'mon, we've gotta
help them out!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[SHINOA grunts]
[gasps]
Hey, Yoichi! Take down
that chopper!
Right!
[YOICHI gasps]
[yells]
[KIMIZUKI yells]
We're clear over here.
We really appreciate
your help. That was intense.
I'm with Shinjuku's
Security Unit.
Well, the third platoon,
to be exact. Corporal Nagai.
And you must be a Vampire
Extermination Unit, right?
Moon Demon Company.
Whoa, you gotta be kidding.
I guess our luck
hasn't run out yet.
Men, ready a transport
for these soldiers.
[OFFICERS]
Sir!
[distant gunfire]
[CORPORAL NAGAI] The vampires
managed to blow a hole
in the western defensive barrier
just before you showed up.
We've got a
counter-attack squad
holding them off
right now, but who knows
how long they'll last.
[SHINOA] Our tactical situation
is much worse than I expected.
[CORPORAL NAGAI] Yes. It's been
a nightmare from the start.
Could your group head west
and reinforce our defenses?
The added support
would be a big help.
[YUICHIRO]
Ya don't have to convince us.
That's the whole
reason we're here.
[CORPORAL NAGAI chuckles]
I guess you're right.
Corporal Nagai.
The vehicle is prepped
and it is ready to go.
[CORPORAL NAGAI] I'll take
them as close as I can
to the western defense.
Remain on high alert.
[OFFICERS grunt]
All right, let's get moving.
[GUREN] Well, lookie here.
It's already started.
The vampires aren't
pullin' any punches.
[GUREN] Now, which one
of them is the commander?
What? You gotta be kidding.
He can see me
from that far away?
[SAYURI]
Um, Lieutenant Colonel Guren?
You don't seem to be too
concerned about this fight.
[GUREN sighs]
It's not like I'm just
slacking off up here, Sayuri.
I'm keeping tabs on
the vampire commander
and enemy troop movements
in case the bastards
decide to target
this outpost as well.
Damn, I should've known,
speaking of the devils.
Watch out.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[MITO grunts]
Took you long enough, Mito.
[MITO]
Are you saying I'm late?
You're the one who called me
here on such short notice.
So, what's with the big hurry?
Guren, sir.
We've returned from our mission.
[NORITO] It looks like things
are going to hell fast.
What do you propose
we do about it?
There's no way the
Extermination Squad
can defeat so many
of them. Can they?
Great. The whole
squad's finally here.
Shigure. How's Yu's team doin'?
They managed to free
all of the civilians.
They've moved on to Shinjuku.
Really? Well done.
They'll be a good addition
to the reinforcement team.
The battlefield is the
best place to grow stronger,
as long as you
don't end up dead.
Okay, it's time
we join this fight.
Pretty sure I know where to
find the vampire commander.
This might be over fast
if we take the leader's head.
What's this? Someone's
got their eyes on us.
[MIKAELA]
Who is it?
Nevermind. Nothing for
you to worry about.
So, how are you feeling?
It's been a while
since you were last here.
You probably have some
bad memories of this place.
But even I must admit
that the humans
built themselves a
pretty impressive city.
Plus, you may even
get a chance to see
your beloved Yu while
you're here. What a bonus.
[grunts]
You're going to drink
his blood, aren't you, Mika?
Go ahead.
[MIKAELA grunts]
[FERID]
You should take advantage
of being on the battlefield,
since it's forbidden
to drink directly
from a human back home.
Ha! And why should
I follow those rules?
They didn't stop you
from drinking my blood.
You didn't hesitate.
Ha! Don't say such things
or you'll hurt my reputation.
Besides, it was you who came
and offered me your
blood that night.
Though,
it was so you could steal a gun
and map from my mansion.
How did that work out for you?
I had no idea that I was
playing into your hands,
or that my family would
be killed to amuse you.
[FERID]
Hm.
[MIKAELA] How many humans
have been slaughtered
just because you
got a little bored?
[FERID]
Oh, Mika...
Why are you still upset
about ancient history?
What's it matter? You're a
vampire yourself now.
[MIKAELA] I'm not upset.
At least, not at you.
I'm angry with myself because
I didn't have the power
to protect my family.
[FERID] Hm. You're a glutton
for self-punishment.
So, how are you
going to protect Yu?
He's the last of your family
in this whole wide world.
That's love!
It could be eternal!
[FERID laughs]
But seriously, Mika.
You really need to drink
a human's blood soon.
You know what happens to
vampires who get too thirsty.
I'd hate for that
to happen to you.
Tch.
[panting, whimpering]
[KRUL] Come on, Mika.
Just drink his blood.
Accept that this
is your life now
and I promise you,
you'll start feeling better.
You'll finally be transformed
into a complete vampire
with an immortal body
and strength far beyond
that of a human.
[MIKAELA grunting] No. No way!
I refuse to become a vampire.
[giggles] You say
that now, but your body
must be craving blood.
[KRUL] I bet every muscle
you have is in pain.
Thirsty, and crying
out for a sip.
[KRUL]
Why do you fight it?
Give your body what it desires.
Shut up!
You're going to waste away.
I'd rather die as a human,
than live as a vampire!
I see.
I'll admit, immortality isn't as
glamorous as one might think.
It can be boring, living for
thousands of years, never aging.
Maybe you've got the right idea.
There's just one problem:
you can't die normally anymore.
[whimpers]
[KRUL] Because I've
changed you for good.
If you don't drink blood,
you'll become a hideous demon.
You'll have no will
or mind of your own.
So you have to drink,
Mika, or else you'll--
[MIKAELA]
There's no way I'll do it!
Never. I will never become
a monster like you!
Well. I'll give you
another option, then.
[gasps]
Drink your fill of my blood.
It's the only other way
that you'll survive.
[MIKAELA gasping, panting]
[KRUL] There's absolutely no
reason for you to refuse this.
Here. Have a little taste.
[MIKAELA grunts]
[MIKAELA]
No. Weren't you listening to me?
I won't ever become one of you!
[KRUL sighs]
[MIKAELA whimpering]
[MIKAELA gasps]
[gasps]
[laughs] That's it. Drink deep.
You're mine now, Mika.
You're never going to
be able to leave me.
[KRUL]
For all eternity.
You're my pet.
My obedient little
blond servant.
Mikaela Hyakuya.
[MIKAELA] I've got ten days'
worth of Krul's blood.
[MIKAELA] I have to find
Yu before I run out.
Before I'm too thirsty.
We should be at
the defensive line
in the next 15 minutes.
Things might get a little bumpy.
There's something we
need to go over
before we get to the
front line. Listen up.
Huh? What is it?
This might sound weird.
But I've got something for you.
It's time for you boys
to take your medicine.
Wait. What medicine?
Are you in charge of
handing out vitamins now?
[SHINOA] Remember how
strong that noble was?
Surely you've realized that he
was way out of our league.
Even with the Black
Demon Series weapons,
he could've slaughtered us
in the blink of an eye.
There'd be nothing left of you!
You will be of
no use to the army
if you're a bunch of corpses.
[SHINOA] Honestly, you'd be
as useless as little babies
with toys if we were
really fighting a noble.
[YUICHIRO]
Why is she smiling?
You're not very reassuring.
So, what do you want us to do?
Well. This is gonna
seem strange,
but I'm sure you'll get
the hang of it quickly.
Then it'll be second
nature. Here we are!
A pill?
[MITSUBA] It's how everybody
gets a little boost
before battle.
Yup.
I hate to say it,
but we're all doping.
It will help in synchronizing
with your demon.
And that means,
your power increases.
So if I take one of those,
I'll be able to kill nobles?
[SHINOA] It's not guaranteed,
but you'd have
a much better chance
of not dying.
One pill and you're
one-and-a-half times stronger.
If you take two,
you're 1.8 times stronger.
That's crazy!
Then if I take,
like, ten of them...
[SHINOA] You'd probably
become some sort of god!
[YOICHI, YUICHIRO,
KIMIZUKI gasp]
Gimme all of them!
[SHINOA]
One thing, though.
Your organs explode
when you take three.
[gasps]
Even two pills will
severely damage your body
and could cause you
to die of shock.
To be safe, you should
stick to one at first.
Also, the effects only
last for 15 minutes.
After the pill wears off,
you'll be just as
vulnerable as you are now.
[SHINOA]
Here. A pack for each of you.
Why didn't you give
these to us earlier?
We could have used 'em
against that noble.
We could've destroyed that guy!
[SHINOA]
We still wouldn't have won.
[gasps]
It takes ten seconds
before the pill's effects
start to take hold. In those
ten seconds we'd be dead.
He could've killed
every single one of us.
One more question.
You mentioned demons earlier.
I definitely wanna max out
my Black Demon Series.
If I take this pill,
will I be able to draw out
the true power
of my Cursed Gear?
[YOICHI, KIMIZUKI grunt]
Sorry. The pill is
just temporary.
You'll have to study
and train more
to master the cursed
power, but we don't
have time for that right now.
Nope! This is war!
So for now, you'll
take a shortcut.
We need every advantage
over the enemy we can get.
You've got a good point.
We could die out there today.
Your glass is always
half-empty, huh?
Hey! I'm just being a realist.
[ALL yelp]
[YOICHI, KIMIZUKI grunt]
[gasps]
Incoming! We've gotta move!
[grunts, gasps]
Corporal!
Be careful!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[SHINOA, YUICHIRO gasp]
Yoichi!
On it!
[YUICHIRO, SHINOA yelp]
[YUICHIRO, SHINOA scream]
[YUICHIRO]
Shinoa.
Hey. Come on. Wake up!
[grunts]
[SHINOA gasps]
[SHINOA]
We fell through to the subway.
[YUICHIRO]
Yeah.
[SHINOA]
Where are the others?
[YUICHIRO] I don't think
they fell with us.
But the corporal here is
banged up pretty badly.
[SHINOA] We need to get him
to the temporary shelter
above ground.
There should be medics there
who can treat his wounds.
[KIMIZUKI]
Hey! Idiot! You down there?
I can hear ya. You okay?
[MITSUBA]
Yeah, of course we are!
There's no way we'd die in
a place like this. Dumbass.
Hey, can you guys get out?
Yeah, No problem!
Then you guys go ahead
and we'll catch up with you.
We've gotta find a med
team for the corporal.
We'll meet you at
the defensive line!
Wait! Shouldn't we...
'Kay, See you at the line.
[rumbling]
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End.
"Results of the Choice."