[YUJI yelps]
[YAMANAKA]
Hey, quit spacing out on us.
Can we go now? This place
gives me the creeps.
Come on, Yuji.
[thump]
[YUJI gasps]
[wind howling]
[STUDENT]
Thanks for coming.
You may not remember me,
but I'm the one
you saved yesterday.
I really can't thank
you enough for that.
[YUICHIRO]
Sure.
I know this is out of the blue,
but would you take this letter?
It would mean so much to me.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Hold on... Is this...?
--[footsteps]
--Uh.
[SHINOA]
My, my.
I guess it's only natural
for the school hero
to become popular
with the girls.
Don't let it go to your head.
In no time, we'll have a trail
of broken hearts to mend.
[YUICHIRO]
Quit talking like you know me.
I'm not a heartbreaker, okay?
[SHINOA]
Ah. I see, so you're a virgin.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Hey! Keep it down!
[SHINOA] These days, virginity
might as well be considered
a mortal sin.
That's why the
Demon Army encourages
everyone to form
new relationships.
It's important that
people "hook-up."
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
The world has already
come to an end once.
Anyone who wasn't
killed by the virus...
...ended up in the belly
of wandering monsters.
We're lucky that even
a tenth of us survived.
[SHINOA] Past those walls are
endless ruins and wastelands,
crawling with all
manner of beasts.
This world of ours: it's no
longer safe for humanity.
[SHINOA] That's where the
Imperial Demon Army comes in.
We'll gather the
remnants of mankind,
and breed our way to the top
of the food chain once again.
Come one and come all!
Get together! Make love!
Yay! Illicit sexual relations!
Yeah, anyway. Can I
ask you something?
[SHINOA]
Mm?
Well, is there a reason
I'm still stuck in this dump?
I already passed Guren's test,
and I've been assigned to the
Vampire Extermination Unit.
So, why am I wasting
time playing schoolboy?
Sorry.
That's a question for the
Lieutenant Colonel, not me.
Then how do I ask him?
That lazy jerk doesn't
even go to his office!
What am I supposed
to do, stalk the guy?
[SHINOA] I don't know why
you're yelling at me.
Do I look like his keeper?
[sighs]
[SHINOA]
Besides,
you don't need to wait
to start your new training.
As a matter of fact,
it's already begun.
Huh?
Our special methods
make the most difficult
of wishes obtainable. Soon,
you will fulfill you desires.
Oh, yeah?
And just what do you
know about my desires?
[SHINOA] I know you
want power. Like this.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[YUICHIRO]
Whoa. What the hell?
[SHINOA] This is the demon
I've formed a contract with.
Shikama Doji.
Try not to embarrass
yourself around him.
Cursed Gear? A weapon
that can kill vampires.
Why do you have one?
Why wouldn't I
have one? I'm a member
of the Extermination Unit,
too, after all.
[YUICHIRO]
It's incredible.
If it was mine, I could
kill any fang I wanted.
Not on your own, you couldn't.
If you want to beat vampires,
you've gotta learn
to work as a team--
[YUICHIRO]
Shinoa!
[SHINOA]
Uh.
I'm taking your Cursed Gear!
[SHINOA gasps]
Just hand it over. I need it
to get revenge for my family.
[SHINOA laughs]
[SHINOA] You can't use
someone else's Gear.
That's why there's a contract.
Then let's see how
well you handle it!
Bring it on, Shinoa!
Fine.
[YUICHIRO grunting]
Not too shabby.
[grunts]
[SHINOA]
But fighting Cursed Gear
with conventional weaponry
won't get you far. See?
[YUICHIRO grunts]
Go, Shi!
[roars]
[whimpers, yelps]
[roaring]
[YUICHIRO groans]
Whoa! Ha, ha. Okay,
that was pretty... badass.
[YUICHIRO]
I don't get it.
You have a kick-ass weapon.
How could a vampire stand
a chance against you?
It's war! When we fight
on the battlefield,
we'll be up against
their soldiers.
There won't be any unarmed
vampires in hospital gowns.
They'll have weapons, too.
[YUICHIRO]
For real? Ugh, that sucks!
They suck. Why do you think
Lieutenant Colonel Guren
has been beating teamwork into
that thick skull of yours?
We cannot win this
without each other.
--[YOICHI] Yu! Help me out here!
--[BOTH gasp]
[YOICHI panting]
[YAMANAKA]
Come on, quit runnin'!
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Don't tell me they're
picking on you again.
[BOTH panting]
We don't want trouble!
Please, hear us out!
Sorry about before.
We were grade-A jerks!
Will you forgive us and
make us your disciples?
Disciples?
[YOICHI]
Now, wait a second.
I can't have any
disciples! No way!
Besides, I don't deserve
that kind of honor!
[YAMANAKA]
Hey, it's you!
Thanks for savin' me yesterday!
[gasps]
My name's Satoshi Yamanaka.
You saved me from
that vampire bitch.
Way to stick it
to her, Boss Man!
"Boss Man"?
[sighs]
Looks like you're
becoming popular
with the male students, too.
I'm starting to feel left out.
So what's with the 180?
You were using Yoichi
as a footrest before.
You've got no right to come back
and start asking him for favors.
Yeah. I can't argue
with you there.
We messed up, okay? But we could
really use his help right now!
[YUICHIRO laughs]
Delinquents these days
seem a little short
in the pride department.
Quit acting like punks
and people might actually
wanna help, ever think of that?
Hello, Pot. Meet my
dear friend, Kettle.
We know we got no
right to ask for help.
Especially after we were
such jerks to you guys.
But, still...
[YUICHIRO]
Still what?
It's Yuji.
The guy who was with us.
He went inside
the Forbidden Chamber
and he never came back out.
The Forbidden Chamber?
That's right.
And, since I heard Yoichi is
joining the Extermination Unit,
I thought...
--[SHINOA] Of course you did.
--[ALL gasp]
I should have guessed.
The words "Class One
Restricted Area" might as well
be a welcome mat to you morons.
No! It's just we... Uh...
[SHINOA]
There's no excuse.
To be honest, I don't
care why you did it.
I care about the punishment.
And as far as the
army's concerned,
your friend's punishment
has already been decided.
What? No way! Are we
talkin' hard time?
I'm sure he's
already in custody.
Oh, no! How long
will he be in there?
Until the army decides
to execute him.
[gasps]
[SHINOA]
I suggest you forget about him.
[footsteps tapping]
[YUICHIRO] So, what's with the
Forbidden Chamber, Shinoa?
Is it some sort of secret lab?
[SHINOA giggles]
No, nothing like that.
It's just one of this
school's Seven Wonders.
Like the piano that plays
concerts all by itself,
or moving anatomical dolls.
Though, I can't remember
if the Chamber is third
or fourth on the list.
You're not as clever
as you might think.
If it's a "Restricted Area,"
the military's got control.
So Yuji somehow
opened the chamber,
and now he's trapped
inside of it?
More than likely.
But that's not the issue.
The room is actually
a training facility
for the Extermination Unit.
If a non-trained civilian,
like Yuji, gets in,
there's a good chance they'll
be possessed by the demon.
Wait... Demon?
[SHINOA]
Remember what I told you?
You don't need to
worry about training
because it's already started.
It's time for us to
move on to the next step.
Now, if you'll follow me.
[YUICHIRO]
Why put a shrine in a school?
And, underground of all places?
[SHINOA]
Well, it isn't really a shrine.
We just like to call it that.
[wind howls]
[SHINOA]
Back before the virus broke out,
a massive underground
space was installed
beneath the Shibuya
part of Tokyo.
Its original purpose
was to prevent
the river from flooding
due to excess rainfall.
[SHINOA]
But now, it's been converted
into the Vampire Extermination
Unit's training grounds.
Then again,
the whole school has.
Basically, every student here
is part of a secret
military experiment.
The demon is the key.
Anyone who's unaffected
by its evil energy
is filtered into the Unit.
[YOICHI gulps]
Every one of us is a lab rat.
It may be hard to hear, but...
What'd you expect in this
messed up world we live in?
[SHINOA]
There are two types of people
who can go beyond this point:
those summoned by the
Extermination Unit,
and those chosen by the demon.
So... Yuji is in there?
[SHINOA]
If he is, we didn't summon him.
The demon may have
already consumed his heart.
And what if it
decides to grab us?
And eats our hearts?
You'd become a ravenous,
man-eating monster, far worse
than any vampire we've faced.
[whimpers]
[SHINOA]
It's not pretty.
That's why you need to be
thoroughly trained, first.
Especially your
strength of heart.
You need to understand the cost
of wielding this Cursed Gear.
That's why I
brought you to--
[YUICHIRO] Point is to
beat the demon, right?
I need power. My family has
waited for revenge long enough.
[YUICHIRO] If this demon
can give me what I need,
I don't care what I
have to do to get it.
[gasps]
Are you crazy?
Don't do anything, understood?
Just watch from a distance.
The Extermination Unit
will save him soon enough.
That's a nice weapon.
Has anybody else claimed it yet?
'Cause if not, then
I'm gonna take it!
[gasps]
[SHINOA]
Wait!
Ugh!
Yoichi! We're gonna need backup.
Go and find the
Moon Demon Company!
Their barracks are at the
back of this facility. Hurry!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[YOICHI]
Right!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
That axe is mine!
Hand it over!
[YUICHIRO roars]
[grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[roars]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[yells]
[grunts]
[YUICHIRO chuckles]
[YUICHIRO]
Man, that thing is badass.
It's weaker than Shinoa's
scythe, but it'll do the job!
--[roaring]
--[YUICHIRO grunts]
Why're you always
getting in my way?
[SHINOA]
Unbelievable.
You must be deathly
allergic to teamwork!
Brute force won't help
you win against a demon.
If you grab that
Gear bare handed,
the demon will
possess you as well.
You'll end up just like Yuji.
I would never lose
to some monster.
You will this time.
You don't have the strength
to defeat a demon, yet.
Wha--?
Your heart is far
too weak to resist it.
Demons thrive on dark desires.
Your hunger for
revenge will make you
that much easier to control.
Do you get it now?
Guren knows you have
excellent combat skills.
But he won't risk
giving you a Cursed Gear
until you've conquered
those feelings!
Is that a challenge?
'Cause I'm sure I
can make that demon
cry out for his mother.
And, now, I'm gonna
prove it to you!
[gasping]
[SHINOA]
What are you doing?
[YUJI, YUICHIRO grunting]
In your face! Now it's mine!
Uh...?
[MIKAELA]
What's up?
Is there something wrong?
Wow, you look pale.
Stop spacing out.
You need to eat before
the food gets cold.
Yeah, hurry up!
Don't let all of my hard
work go to waste, Yu.
[KOUTA]
I'm hungry, bro! Come on!
[CHIHIRO]
It's really tasty!
Uh, okay.
[AKANE] Here. There's plenty,
so don't hold back.
[MIKAELA]
Isn't this great, everyone?
Yu is actually with us today!
Yup.
[AKO] He needs to come over
every day from now on!
[MIKAELA]
Oh.
So I've been wondering, how's
the revolution coming along?
Huh?
What? Don't tell me
you forgot about it!
You swore you'd become
stronger than the vampires
then you'd free us and make
a new home for all humanity.
[AKO]
That's right, Yu! You did!
We'll be waiting for you
to keep your promise, okay?
And don't forget,
you need your strength
to save the world,
so be sure to eat up!
She's right, Yu! Eat your fill!
Don't be shy, there's more
than enough to share.
[YUICHIRO]
Y-Yeah, sure.
Quick question.
Are you alive or am I dreaming?
[MIKAELA]
We're all dead.
You watched Ferid
murder us, remember?
[CHIHIRO]
You saw it happen!
[TAICHI]
We're D-E-D!
[AKO]
What's wrong with him?
He keeps forgetting things!
That mean vampire noble ripped
our bodies limb from limb.
The only one that ran
away from him was you.
I didn't run away!
I tried to save you!
[MIKAELA]
You abandoned us.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
[MIKAELA]
It's been four years
and you still haven't
avenged our deaths.
It's not too late
to change that.
You can still get revenge
for us, and set things right.
If you'd like, I could
lend you my power.
Accept my gift
with all your heart
and vengeance will be yours.
Vengeance.
[MIKAELA]
Yes. For all of us.
[YUICHIRO]
You're right.
I need power to get back
at those parasites.
Very well.
Open your heart and you'll
get justice for your family.
[YUICHIRO]
But you're not my family.
[MIKAELA gasps]
--[YUICHIRO grunts]
--[MIKAELA gasps]
Just who are you?
You're not the Mika that I know!
[YUICHIRO]
He's not like me.
He'd never tell me
to live for vengeance
or try to make me feel guilty!
He'd tell me to be smart.
Then he'd go behind my back
and shoulder all
the burden himself,
because that's just
the kind of friend he was!
[YUICHIRO whimpers]
But I'm still here.
I'm done playing!
Now who the hell are you?
[wood cracking]
Stop, Yu. Listen!
Shut your mouth!
Trying to trick me with
Mika's face was a huge mistake!
No more games! Tell me
how you know so much
about my precious
family, you bastard!
[roars]
Ah.
Okay...
So.. why am I
lying on the floor?
I can't believe it.
You managed to come
back all on your own.
Come back from where, exactly?
[BOTH]
Uh...
The demon, it tricked you.
It had you trapped inside
some intense hallucinations.
[gasps]
But, even without
a contract spell,
you broke free with
the power of your mind.
That's quite an accomplishment.
Yeah... I have no idea
what you're saying.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO] So, does this
axe belong to me now?
[SHINOA] No, it's a little
more involved than that.
There are procedures to follow
when you form a new contract.
Guren will decide which
Gear suits you best.
You're just gonna
have to be patient.
But I still kicked
some demon ass, right?
Uh.
Yeah... Technically.
[YUICHIRO] And this is the
second time I've beaten
the Moon Demon Company
to the rescue.
Well... yeah... I guess
you have a point.
[SHINOA] On top of that,
you saved another classmate.
[SHINOA] You won't have
to wait much longer.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll begin your training
with the rest of the
Vampire Extermination Unit.
[YUICHIRO]
All right!
[SHINOA] Not that I have the
authority to make that decision.
Guren won't be happy
when he finds out.
[YUICHIRO]
Finally...
I've made it this far.
It won't be long now.
[YUICHIRO]
Starting tomorrow,
I'm killing every last
vampire I come across.
[FERID]
Mika, Mika, my sweet Mika!
[FERID chuckles]
Hello. I had a feeling
that I would find you here.
Have you heard
the latest report?
[FERID] Apparently,
they finally tracked down
your precious angel. I told you
it was only a matter of time.
No one can stay hidden forever.
As we feared,
he's become a puppet
for those filthy humans.
What's his name?
[FERID]
Yuichiro, wasn't it?
I wonder.
How will you weave the next part
of this tragic tale,
my dear Mikaela?
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
"Vampire Mikaela."