[SHINOA]
We fell through to the subway.
[YUICHIRO]
Yeah.
[SHINOA]
Where are the others?
[YUICHIRO]
I don't think they fell with us.
But the corporal here is
banged up pretty badly.
[SHINOA] We need to get
him to the temporary shelter
above ground.
There should be medics there
who can treat his wounds.
[KIMIZUKI]
Hey! Idiot! You down there?
I can hear ya. You okay?
[MITSUBA]
Yeah, of course we are!
There's no way we'd die in
a place like this. Dumbass.
Hey, can you guys get out?
Yeah, no problem!
Then you guys go ahead
and we'll catch up with you.
We've gotta find a med
team for the corporal.
We'll meet you at
the defensive line!
Wait! Shouldn't we...
'Kay, see you at the line.
[rumbling]
[GUREN]
Well, dammit.
I didn't kill the
commander after all.
[FERID chuckles]
Impressive.
That attack took out a whole
squadron of our men.
It looks like the
humans are sending in
their strongest forces.
Strongest forces?
[FERID] These soldiers are with
the Vampire Extermination Unit's
most elite squad.
The Moon Demon Company.
All right, everyone.
[FERID] Are you ready to end
this war once and for all?
Then let's slaughter
the livestock.
Full-blown extermination.
[GUREN]
Let me ask you somethin'.
Do you really like the
taste of human blood?
Or is this a twisted reenactment
of the Last Supper?
Lend me your power.
Demon Blade: Mahiru-no-yo.
[GUREN]
Don't hold back!
This is the fight that
you've been training for.
Protect this line.
Kill every one of 'em.
[AKANE] C'mon, slowpokes,
it's time to go!
[KIDS]
Okay!
We're heading out, so you guys
hold down the fort, all right?
[YUICHIRO]
Sure.
[MIKAELA]
Have fun!
[AKO]
Bye-bye!
[TAICHI]
See ya later!
[KOUTA] Lunch time is my
favorite time of day!
[AKO]
I'm so hungry!
[TAICHI]
My stomach's rumbling!
[AKANE]
Careful, now.
You're gonna trip over
someone if you rush like that.
[door creaks]
[MIKAELA]
Hey, Yu. What's up?
Can't you see
that I'm reading?
[MIKAELA] Aw, c'mon,
take a break for a sec.
What is with you?
You're being annoying.
If we could escape from this
place, what would you wanna do?
Where would you wanna go?
Huh?
Did you hit your
head or somethin'?
We can't escape 'cause
the virus would kill us
as soon as we got outside.
[MIKAELA]
Use your imagination.
If we could escape
to the outside
with the rest of the family.
If we could go to a place
without any vampires,
then don't you think
we would have fun?
Without vampires?
[MIKAELA]
Yeah, just us family.
Sure, that sounds great,
but it's impossible.
[MIKAELA]
You'd be happy?
Yeah, of course I would.
[chuckles] Then I guess I'd
better get busy working on that.
On what?
[MIKAELA]
Mm-mm! It's a secret.
Well. I've got some
errands I need to run.
Errands? What do you have to do?
[MIKAELA] If I told you,
it'd ruin the surprise.
Uh...
What a weirdo.
[YUICHIRO]
Unfortunately,
Mika didn't escape the
way he thought he would.
[YUICHIRO] And it turned out the
world beyond was no paradise.
We should go meet the others.
But the corporal...
He'll be fine here.
The doctors say he's
going to recover
That's good. I'm glad.
Besides, Lieutenant
Colonel Guren has issued
some new orders
for our squadron.
[YUICHIRO gasps]
Guren's in Shinjuku?
That's right.
He's reorganizing our
troops within the city.
The Lieutenant Colonel
is already ahead of us
at West Shinjuku
and Fifth Street.
He's been fighting the
vampires' main forces there.
We need to go back him up.
The main forces.
If we can crush them,
then the vampires will be
defeated and we'll win this.
[SHINOA]
They're probably thinking
the same thing about us.
If they crush the Moon Demon
Company, victory is theirs.
We should get moving.
Mitsu and the others
have probably made it to
the defensive line by now.
[COMMANDER 9A]
I told you, it's not possible!
Our orders are to send
everyone we've got to
the defensive line.
If the vampires get through
there, Shinjuku will fall.
But our troops are
gonna be wiped out here
if we don't help them.
So send in the
Extermination Unit.
They're teenaged kids and
there's only three of them!
I thought they were supposed
to have five members.
The enemy has sent a
high-ranking platoon
--to annihilate them.
--[SHINOA] Hey, Yu, wait!
They're going to die.
It's only a matter of time.
[sighs] All right, fine.
I can spare a few men.
Tell me the location of--
What were you saying?
That Extermination Unit.
Was it The Moon Demon Company?
[TROOPER 10A]
Um, I dunno. Maybe?
Why, who are you?
[SHINOA]
We're part of the Moon Demon--
[YUICHIRO] Wait. You said
there were three of them.
Is it a girl and two guys?
Yeah, are you
with them or what?
[YUICHIRO] Look, I just
need you to tell me
where they're fighting.
[TROOPER 10A] They're at
Shinjuku Central Park.
[YUICHIRO]
All right.
We're gonna go help them.
Send everyone else to the
defensive line, got it?
Let's go.
Hey! Wait a minute!
[SHINOA]
You're not thinking clearly.
You can't even be sure that he
was talking about our squad.
We can't ignore our orders
based on speculation.
We're needed as backup.
That's our top priority.
Even Lieutenant Colonel Guren
will have a hard time
going up against the
vampires' strongest forces.
We have to maintain
Shinjuku's defensive line.
Guren is counting
on us to be there.
So are the rest of his troops.
[GUREN yelling]
[TROOPERS yelling]
[hisses]
[GUREN grunts]
There's no end to
these bloodsuckers.
Mito and I can
keep them occupied
while you go after
the commander.
When did you get so
good at strategizing?
Let's do it.
This fight's finally
getting interesting.
It's a shame that Crowley,
the Thirteenth Progenitor,
isn't here. He would
make this a battle
truly worthy of
the history books.
He's really missing out.
Lacus. Rene.
Round up our men and
take down all the humans
except for the one in charge.
Sir.
Consider it done.
Well, Mika.
Maybe now I'll finally
get a chance to see
Krul Tepes's favorite
servant in action.
You must be very thirsty.
[MIKAELA grunts]
You and I can kill their
pompous leader together.
What do ya say?
I can do this on my own.
Think so? Then he's all yours.
He will regret coming
to attack me.
It will be his undoing.
My sword.
Oh. How intimidating.
I think we're
almost there, Yu!
Yeah!
[YUICHIRO]
Thank you.
[SHINOA]
Hm?
[YUICHIRO]
For coming.
Well, we are a family.
And it's just like Lieutenant
Colonel Guren told us.
We have to protect
each other, no matter what.
--[SHINOA] Idiot.
--What?
That's what he would call you.
[YUICHIRO]
Heh. He probably would.
[SHINOA] There it is.
Shinjuku Central Park.
[KIMIZUKI pants]
[pants]
[gasps]
Yoichi! Behind you!
Huh?
Dammit!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[VAMPIRE grunts, groans]
[pants] Are we really this weak
without shorty and the
dumbass backing us up?
We can't complete a
formation without them.
[pants]
[pants] Get ready!
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
Don't underestimate me!
Kimizuki! Watch your back!
Goodbye.
Look, it's Yu!
[MITSUBA]
Huh?
[grunts]
[SHINOA] Don't get distracted
on the battlefield, Mitsu.
Where are the rest
of the vampires?
They're all dead, genius.
Actually, you just killed
the last one of 'em.
[YUICHIRO]
Huh?
[gasps] Well, damn, you guys.
Looks like you're pretty
amazing after all.
You must've forgotten how
good I am at killing vamps.
Hey, shouldn't you
be backing up Guren?
[YUICHIRO]
What are you talking about?
I heard you were in a tight
spot, so I came to make sure
you didn't get
backed into a corner.
You didn't need to do that.
Besides, we said we'd meet
you at the defensive line.
That was your plan.
Sure, that was the plan.
But I just thought...
What? That we would fail?
Did you honestly
think we didn't
have the strength and training
to take down an enemy platoon?
You've gotta learn
to trust your family.
You're right. My bad.
[KIMIZUKI]
Yeah, well,
don't go making the same
mistake in the future.
Okay?
Sorry but if it was to
happen again tomorrow,
I'd still come running.
You what?
Did you hear anything
I just said?
It's not that I don't trust you
or think that you're weak.
It's just that I care.
[KIMIZUKI grunts]
[YUICHIRO]
I'd do it tomorrow.
The day after... Forever.
[sighs] What was I thinking?
I must've forgotten what a
hardcore dumbass you can be.
You shouldn't bother wasting
your breath with him, Kimizuki.
You can't fix his
brand of stupid.
[KIMIZUKI]
You're right.
Seems the more we try,
the dumber he gets.
[YUICHIRO]
Oh, come on, guys!
They're just kidding.
[MITSUBA]
Huh?
[SHINOA]
The sun is finally out.
Now that we've
cleaned out the park,
we should probably
catch up with Guren.
Yeah, you're right.
And we can go as a full squad!
[SHINOA]
Ready, Yu?
Hell yeah, let's move!
We're gonna kill every one of
those bloodsucking bastards!
[distant swords clanging]
[distant gunfire, explosions]
[TROOPERS yelling]
[SAYURI, MITO grunting]
[GUREN, MIKAELA grunting]
Well, well. You're a strong one.
A challenge, at last.
Yes. But not one
that you will win.
[grunts]
Explode, now. Fudo Myo-o Spell.
Tsk, tsk. Landing a
curse on your head.
I thought that you'd be faster.
I evaded the blast...
And besides, do you really
think old school spell craft
works on vampires?
[FERID chuckles]
Mika. Just as I expected.
Tremendous power
and overconfidence.
If you're not careful,
that arrogance will get the rug
pulled out from under you.
Do you need a hand?
What are you getting at?
There's no way
I'll lose against him.
[FERID]
The rug underneath you.
[gasps]
[FERID] You see, our
enemies never intended
to fight us one-on-one.
They've caught on, Shigure.
Kill them.
[SHIGURE]
Yes, Sir.
[gasps]
Goshi. The Illusionary Spell.
Already on it.
[sighs]
[GUREN]
And this is checkmate, vampire!
There, Mika. Now you owe me one.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[GUREN groaning]
[GUREN groans]
[GUREN coughs]
Damn. It's worse than I thought.
[GUREN] The silver-haired
one must be a noble.
He's way too strong.
Remember, Mika.
It's always a mistake to
underestimate the livestock.
There's nothing honorable
about the way
these greedy little
blood bags fight.
Although, I guess you
know all about that
as an ex-human yourself.
Shut up.
Ha! Well.
We should probably get
serious about this.
Let's fight together.
[MIKAELA]
I don't need your help.
I know what their
strategy is now.
My sword. Drink more
of my blood.
Heh... There's that
arrogance again.
It's an unfortunate holdover
from your humanity
that's going to get
you in trouble one day.
Looks like I'll have to take
two pills to pull this one off.
Don't risk it,
Lieutenant Colonel!
Distraction will get
you killed, little girl.
Speak for yourself.
[gasps]
[gasps] Oh, wow.
Not bad.
[SAYURI]
Please! Put the pills away!
If you die of shock from
taking two of them,
then you can't lead us.
But if I don't take 'em,
we'll all end up dead.
The clock is ticking.
We have to kill them before
the pills' effects wear off.
[MIKAELA]
Are you done talking yet?
I want to get this over with.
[GUREN] Heh. Well aren't
you a polite vampire?
Would you let us have a
little more time to regroup?
[MIKAELA]
How much more?
It's time for us to
take our medicine,
so if you could be quiet for
just 20 seconds or so we'd--
[GUREN grunts]
Well, you can't blame
a guy for tryin'.
And is it just me, or are you
a lot faster than before?
I'm not holding anything
back from now on.
[GUREN grunts]
Holding back on the battlefield?
Sounds like the
strategy of a child.
You shouldn't taunt someone
stronger than you.
It's not smart.
[GUREN, MIKAELA grunt]
Damn you.
[GUREN]
I guess this is it.
Uh-- Oh.
Looks like his
backup has arrived.
Go on, Mika.
Put the poor man
out of his misery.
[gasps]
Not good! He's been cornered!
Quick, everyone,
take your pill!
We'll save the Lieutenant
Colonel and then retreat!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
This is the end, human.
Do it then.
Guren!
[gasps]
You damn vampire!
You get away from him right now.
[MIKAELA]
Another reckless human.
What annoying pests.
No way...
Is... that...?
[gasps]
[MIKAELA]
Yu?
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End.
"Reunion of Childhood Friends."