[WOMAN 1A] We can pick
some up on the way home.
[WOMAN 1A]
Huh--?
[gasps]
--[groans]
--[car horn blares]
[tires screech]
[alarm ringing]
[distant car alarm blares]
--[DOG 1A barks]
--[YUICHIRO whimpers]
[FISHMONGER 1A gasping]
[FISHMONGER 1A groans]
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCEMENT 1A]
Your attention, please.
A deadly virus has been
unleashed to punish humanity
for its foolishness.
There is no cure.
Your last night is upon you.
[pants]
Mika. I don't think
she's breathing.
Keep them over there, Yu!
Director? Can you hear me?
[ALL gasp]
[ANNOUNCEMENT 1A]
However, we have chosen
to spare the young.
This virus will not affect
anyone 13 or younger.
The direct unit of the
Third Progenitor, Krul Tepes,
is currently collecting the
children of this district.
From this day forward, you shall
be under our protection.
[gasps]
[AKANE, TAICHI gasp]
[AKANE whimpers]
Who's next?
[YUICHIRO]
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
[VAMPIRE 1A]
Okay, next.
Mikaela Hyakuya.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Ugh...
[YUICHIRO yells]
[MIKAELA] Stop wasting it.
Do you wanna get sick?
It's nasty. I won't
drink this crap.
[sighs] You need to
quit bein' so picky.
And you need to quit doing
what the fangs tell you.
I don't think it's all
that bad, to be honest.
Seriously?!
[MIKAELA]
At least we're alive.
And more importantly, we get
to live with our family.
Don't you think that's enough?
I'm not their livestock.
[MIKAELA] Ugh. It's like
talking to wall with you.
That stubborn streak won't keep
them away from your neck--
Hey!
[gasps]
[BOY 1A, GIRL 1B groan]
Ah! Yu, no! Don't!
[YUICHIRO yelps]
Apologize! Do it, or else!
[MIKAELA]
Please, sir! Ignore him.
You see, he's just
a harmless moron!
[YUICHIRO]
What?
I'll take care of him. I swear
this won't happen again.
[YUICHIRO]
Can it, Mika!
I'm in the middle of
kicking this guy's ass--
[YUICHIRO gagging]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[FERID]
What's going on here?
[MIKAELA gasps]
[YUICHIRO grunts, coughs]
No hood. Is he a noble?
[MIKAELA]
Lord Ferid!
[gasps]
Ah! Young Mika. What's
all the fuss about?
[MIKAELA]
Oh, nothing.
Just one of my family members
causing trouble again.
That must be so stressful.
Poor Mika. I know!
Won't don't you come by
my mansion again tonight?
I would like that!
[FERID]
As would I, dear boy.
You have such sweet blood.
You're always welcome.
And will the troublemaker
be joining us?
Huh? Like hell I--
Oh, I don't know if that's
a good idea. He's shy.
[FERID]
What a shame. Maybe next time.
Hm.
You just had to go and
butt in, didn't you?
I had that parasite right
where I wanted him.
You can't really believe that.
'Fess up.
You know we don't have a prayer
against the vampires.
They're too strong for us.
We won't know for sure
till we give it a try!
Yeah, yeah. You keep
fooling yourself.
Look, I get that you're angry,
but you need to be
more careful, okay?
If Lord Ferid hadn't
shown up, you'd be dead.
'Bout that. He seemed
to know you pretty well.
Of course he does.
We have a deal.
I give him blood and he
gives me whatever I want.
Plus, he serves
dinner when I visit.
It might seem wrong
to you, but you've gotta
use your head if you wanna
survive in this place.
[MIKAELA grunts]
Yu, wait. Isn't there
anything you want?
[YUICHIRO]
Not from you!
Ah! I had a feeling
I'd find you here.
Why aren't you with Mika?
Did you two have another fight?
That good for nothing?
He's an idiot.
Okay. Do you wanna
talk about it?
Just leave me alone,
and don't sit so close.
Why not? We're family.
It's not weird or anything.
I don't have a
family, so it is.
Yes, you do!
Everyone from the Hyakuya
Orphanage's is one big family!
It's true 'cause the
director said so!
That's stupid.
[DIRECTOR 1A]
Attention, everyone!
Yuichiro here is
the newest member
of our little family.
So make him feel welcome.
Be on your best behavior, okay?
'Kay!
[YUICHIRO grunts]
[MIKAELA]
Hey, Yu.
My name's Mikaela.
I'm an orphan too,
so I know how you feel.
I was sad at first, but now
I have a big family!
If you like, you can
be a part of it.
[YUICHIRO] You think that
means anything to me?
You wanna know why I'm here?
'Cause my dad went crazy
and tried to kill me.
And my mom?
She was so convinced
I was a "demon child"
that she committed suicide.
You think you know how I feel?
Well, you don't!
Keep your "family," I don't
want any part of it--
[MIKAELA] Wow. That must
have been really hard.
But starting today, everything
is gonna get better.
[bell tolls]
[AKANE]
Well, let's get going.
Dinner's almost ready.
And everyone's waiting
on you, Mr. Moody.
Come on, you can be
grumpy at the table.
[FUMIE]
Yu's home!
--Yay! It's time for food!
--[AKO] Finally! I'm starving!
--[TAICHI] Yu! Hi!
--[YUICHIRO] Careful. Jeez.
You act like I was
lost or something.
Guess what?
There's a big surprise
in the kitchen!
Akane's making curry!
With real meat and everything!
Oh yeah?
[YUICHIRO]
Where'd you get all that?
Crazy, isn't it?
I thought I was gonna faint
when Mika brought it to me.
I'm excited!
I've never had a chance to cook
a feast like this before!
What an idiot.
[KIDS munching, chatting]
[KOUTA]
Yummy!
[CHIHIRO]
It's so good!
Why aren't you
eating anything?
You not hungry?
--Nah.
--[TAICHI] Aw, yuck!
[TAICHI]
There are carrots in here!
Hey, Akane! Guess what?
Today's actually my birthday!
Well, whaddya know?
It's my birthday, too!
No fair! I want one!
I do, too!
I have no choice then.
I officially declare today
everyone's birthday!
--[KOUTA] For real?
--[CHIHIRO] Awesome! Yay!
Remember to thank Mika
whenever he gets home.
Will do!
Why isn't he here for dinner?
Does he not like curry?
Where is Mika?
Do you know, Yu?
Sorry, I don't.
[FUMIE gasps]
Taichi ate my curry!
[AKANE] Then Taichi can
give up the rest of his.
[TAICHI]
Aw, man!
[KIDS giggle]
[TAICHI]
Why do I always get in trouble?
[door creaks]
[gasps]
Aw. You stayed up? I'm touched.
Whatever.
Don't tell me you're
still angry with me.
Course not. I ate your
curry, so we're even.
Huh?
I'm kidding.
All the kids really
enjoyed it, though.
[MIKAELA chuckles]
So, what'd you have to do?
I mean, to get the curry.
Idiot.
Next time, we're
trading my blood.
[MIKAELA] Come on, nobody
wants your nasty blood.
[gasps]
[MIKAELA]
Kidding. Forget about it.
You need to focus on
defeating the vampires.
Just leave the rest to me.
[YUICHIRO]
Stop it!
You can't take on all
of the burden by yourself.
I'm not stupid.
I know how strong
the vampires are.
I know that beating
them is impossible--
[MIKAELA]
I don't wanna hear it.
These kids look up to you.
They hang on your every word.
"We can beat the fangs."
"We won't lose."
It gives them hope.
It gives all of us hope.
Now, let's get some grub.
Here. Make sure you
actually eat, this time.
[YUICHIRO] No, it's yours.
I don't want any.
[MIKAELA]
Too bad.
[MIKAELA chuckles] That's not
a request. It's an order.
Why do I have to take
orders from you?
'Cause, if you don't
keep your strength up,
you won't kill as many
fangs with this bad boy.
You're not done until you've
licked the bowl clean.
Whoa.
[MIKAELA] If you think that's
impressive, check this out.
Tadaa! A map of the city!
It even shows us where
all the exits are!
Hang on. Did you steal
this from the noble?
Ferid's mansion is
as big as a castle.
It took forever just
to find anything useful.
The great Mikaela doesn't
give his blood away
for a pat on the back.
He gets his dues.
Anyway, that all stops now.
We're leaving tonight.
[MIKAELA] I already know
what you're gonna say.
But don't worry, I've got
it all planned out.
Just leave it to
the Great Mikaela!
[YUICHIRO]
But what about the virus?
We could die as soon
as we get outside!
We won't get infected
as long as we're 13
or younger, remember?
Any idea how old we are now?
[YUICHIRO]
Twelve, I think?
Then that gives us a
whole year to find a cure.
I think we can do it.
As long as the Hyakuya
family works together,
everything'll turn out okay.
I can't figure out if
you really have a plan
or if you're just
making all this up.
I don't know, it sounds risky.
[AKANE]
What are you doing?
Huh?
Why are you still awake?
Oh! Mika! Hi.
You ate!
So what'd you think
of the curry, Yu?
Okay, Mika. Let's do it.
Great! Let's go!
Akane, go wake everybody up.
Why?
It's time we said
goodbye to this city!
[door thuds]
Clear.
[gasps]
[KIDS]
Wow!
[AKO]
Where are we going, anyway?
[FUMIE]
I don't like the dark.
[KOUTA] Won't we get in
trouble for being outside?
[MIKAELA]
Don't worry, it's fine.
It won't be long before we're
saying "bye-bye" to this world.
[FUMIE]
Huh? Why?
I don't get it,
where are we going?
Tell them, Yu.
We're going back to
the human world!
And guess what? We can
have curry every day!
[CHIHIRO]
Really?
[AKO] I wanna have
birthday cake every day!
What about hamburgers?
Sh.
[sighs]
It looks like
we're almost there.
All right! We're in
the final stretch!
[KIDS giggle, cheer]
Let's go.
Yeah!
[FERID chuckles]
Hello, little lambs.
I was beginning to
wonder if you'd show up.
[FERID]
Aw, just look at those faces.
I love the expression
humans make
when all of their hopes
have been dashed.
It's so intoxicating that I
can't stop playing this game.
What "game"?
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[FERID]
What a pity. It died so quickly.
[growls] Damn you!
[gasps]
[FERID] Well, well. I believe
that is my pistol.
Sneaking it past me took a
cunning that few possess.
I'm impressed, Mika.
I never expected to be
this entertained.
It makes me hungry for more.
Does that fire of yours
need rekindling?
What if I told you that map you
stole was the genuine article?
All you have to do
is make it past me
and you'll be back
in your world.
It'll be hard to chase you
once you've made it outside.
The question is whether or
not you can make it there.
Get going!
[KIDS whimper]
Move it!
[KIDS scream]
Yes, that's it.
Go! We'll hold him off!
[KIDS screaming]
[gasps]
I'm begging you...
Leave them alone!
[whimpering]
Akane, run!
Let me savor the
misery as you lose
everything you hold dear.
[MIKAELA]
It's okay, Yu. Don't forget.
The two of us, we're family.
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO]
Hey!
[laughs] Sweet Mikaela.
I'll miss your
company most of all.
And the lovely meals.
[grunts]
Run... Yu.
[gasps]
Die.
[pants]
Mika!
Hey! Look at me!
Go, Yu. Leave me here.
[YUICHIRO]
Don't be stupid!
We're going back
together! Remember?
Don't let us die for nothing.
Shut up! You're fine!
You're gonna
make it! Come on.
Mika, I can't leave, I can't!
I finally have a family!
[YUICHIRO]
I won't lose you!
[MIKAELA grunting]
Just go, you idiot! Now!
[gasps]
[sobs]
[YUICHIRO grunts]
That was, the first time
he called us family.
[YUICHIRO screams]
[YUICHIRO sobbing]
[screams]
[gasps]
[YUICHIRO panting]
[GUREN]
Good, he's here.
[gasps]
The prophecy was right.
It was foretold that we
would come into contact
with one of the test
subjects from Hyakuya Labs.
Hey, kid.
How would you like
to help us get rid
of the vampires
once and for all?
--[gasps]
--[YUICHIRO sobbing]
I'll do whatever it takes.
[sighs]
[YUICHIRO sobs]
[YUICHIRO] As long as I get to
kill every last one of 'em.
[YUICHIRO]
Next time, on Seraph of the End.
"Humanity After the Fall."