[Narrator]
They call it the Dragon Age‐‐
a time of political strife,
savage beasts and
powerful magic‐‐
but also a time of faith‐‐
faith in the Chantry
of Andraste,
a dominant religious order led
by her holiness, the Divine...
Her Templar knights exert
harsh control over the Mages,
restricting the practice of
the arcane magical arts
they believe have the potential
to unleash a blight
upon the world...
The most dangerous of these are
the Blood Mages who continue
to perform their
dark rituals in secret...
in defiance of the Chantry.
Determined to neutralize
this threat at any cost,
the Templar's methods
become more brutal
and their suspicions rise,
even extending to
the loyal Circle of Magi...
Corruption infects
the Templar ranks
as the leadership
sees their role shift
from control and protection...
to suppression.
As tensions boil
within the Chantry,
the balance of power
has been maintained
by the Seekers, the finest
and most loyal of the Templars.
Handpicked by
the Divine herself...
...these defenders of
truth root out corruption,
wherever it may be found,
be it from rogue Mages,
or within the halls
of the Chantry itself.
Now the "Ten Year Gathering
of the Faithful" looms,
and pilgrims from all
corners of the world
journey to the Orlaisian
Empire to pray for peace...
A peace that those in the
shadows are plotting to shatter.
[bird hooting and
crickets chirping]
[drum beat]
[dragon growls]
[dragon roars]
[dragon roars in pain]
Brothers!
A new era for Mages
everywhere is about to begin!
[Blood Mages cheer]
[dragon roars]
[Frenic] Now, Avexis, the time
has come to join our cause.
[Avexis struggles, gulps]
[Avexis grunts]
[Avexis cries sharply]
[Avexis pants]
[Byron] Keep your focus,
Cassandra.
Don't let your fury run
away with you again.
I know, Byron.
Trust in the Maker.
[Avexis takes a breath]
[Frenic] It's useless
to resist, Avexis.
Drink.. Drink your destiny...
[Blood Mage] Brother Frenic...
If she drinks any more,
it will kill her...
[Blood Mage chokes]
I will decide when she's had
enough. Is that understood?!
[battle cries from the Seekers]
[Byron] For the Chantry!
[Seekers] For the Chantry!
[Seekers yell]
[Cassandra breathes heavily]
[Cassandra] Ha!
[Seekers and Blood Mages
grunt, struggle]
[Frenic snarls]
[Frenic] Now, release it!
[dragon growls]
[dragon roars]
[Cassandra yells repeatedly]
[Byron] Enough, Cassandra!
Gather your wits.
We have work to do.
[dragon growls]
[dragon roars]
[Byron] I'll draw its eye.
Don't keep me waiting!
[Byron] Hey!
That's right! Come on!
Come and get me!
[dragon roars]
[Cassandra yells]
[dragon roars in pain]
[Seeker D] There's
nowhere left to run, Mage.
[Seeker E]
Release the girl and submit!
[Cassandra] Make way!
You're from one of the
dragon‐hunting clans.
It seems I'm outmatched...
Spineless Blood Mage!
You may rise.
[Divine] We applaud your
recent efforts, High Seeker.
However, your report
also raises many concerns.
To think this is all
happening so close
to the Ten Year Gathering...
Surely it is not a coincidence.
We're already taking
extra precautions, Most Holy.
So you managed to bring back
a little Blood Mage girl?
Avexis is not a Blood Mage,
Your Grace.
She was taken from
the Circle of Magi.
[First Enchanter] It's true.
She went missing from
the Circle a few weeks ago.
Presumably kidnapped. We've
been searching for her since.
I am most grateful for
her rescue, High Seeker.
We will come for her soon.
I'm afraid I cannot allow that,
First Enchanter.
And why not?
[High Seeker] She was
the focus of the ritual,
and is obviously vital
to whatever the Blood
Mages are planning.
She will remain in my custody
until we get to
the bottom of this.
Did the Seekers really
bring down a drake?
Yes, Your Reverence.
It was Cassandra.
[Divine] You are to be commended
for your exceptional bravery.
I would expect nothing
less from a Pentaghast.
Your family's dragon‐hunting
skills are legendary.
You honor us, Grand Cleric. We
are proud to serve the Chantry.
[Knight Commander, clapping]
You have my praise as well,
High Seeker.
Another notable success
by your loyal order.
However, it seems
rather reckless
to risk your small numbers
against Blood Mage ceremonies.
Perhaps if you shared
your intelligence,
my Templars could
better assist you.
There are times when stealth
and discretion are more
valuable than numbers.
Are you implying you don't
trust us to act with discretion?
Ensuring that you do
is one of our duties.
Or have you forgotten,
Knight Commander?
Gentlemen,
remember where you are.
My deepest apologies,
Your Holiness.
With your permission,
we shall take our leave and
return to our investigation.
[Cassandra grunts repeatedly]
[Cassandra pants]
[Byron] Such violence before
bed will give you nightmares.
Let's see what you've got!
[Cassandra and Byron
grunt repeatedly]
[Cassandra and
Byron breathe heavily]
[Byron] There's nothing left for
me to teach you about swordplay.
I know no man tougher
than you with a blade.
[Cassandra, with a laugh]
But you just bested me.
Yes, but you weren't fighting
with everything you
have, were you?
[Cassandra] Perhaps, but you had
me completely at your mercy
with that final move.
Sometimes your blade
becomes your shield
and your shield
becomes your blade.
Your prejudice misleads
your judgment, Cassandra.
To see the truth, you must look
through the eyes of your heart,
and not just the
ones in your head.
Not everything is what it
appears on the surface.
[laughing] Sorry, I must sound
just like a father
lecturing his child.
I'd be proud to have
you as a father.
Good night, Byron.
[Frenic] One of the
Circle of Magi dogs
was able to sniff
out our ritual.
However, its purpose
still eludes them.
As long as we get Avexis back,
we can proceed as planned.
It's far too dangerous to
continue meeting like this.
[Frenic] Here.
This is a rare Elven Stone
you can use
to communicate with me.
Keep it on your
person at all times.
Should you discover any
more useful information,
my Mages and
I will be ready to act.
Victory will be ours.
[Frenic chuckles]
[young man pants]
[Cassandra gasps]
[Byron gasps]
[Cassandra]
Byron! What are you doing?
There's no time to explain.
Go back to your quarters and
forget what you've seen here.
That's not what you
trained me to do.
[Byron] I trained you
to follow orders. Now go!
Byron!
[Cassandra]
Tell me where you're taking her.
I can't say.
I'm on an important mission.
[Cassandra] What is it?
I don't want to involve
you in this.
[Seeker] Raise the alarm! Men
down! There's been an intruder!
[Seekers]
‐‐Someone has taken the girl!
‐‐Search the grounds!
‐‐Find her!
‐‐They can't have gotten far!
[Byron] Come on.
[Byron pants]
[Seeker B2] Byron and Cassandra
have taken the girl!
[Seeker A] Inform
the High Seeker.
The rest of you, follow me!
[Seekers] Hya!
[Byron pants]
[Cassandra pants]
[Byron] We'll wait here.
For what?
Byron!
[Byron] Yes... I suppose
you're a part of this now...
I don't know all
the details yet,
but I've been
investigating a conspiracy.
That's how I found out about
the Blood Mage ceremony.
Is the High Seeker
aware of this?
No... I fear the conspiracy goes
all the way to the Chantry.
And you suspect
the High Seeker?!
I'm a Seeker.
I'm trained to suspect everyone.
[Cassandra] Do you even know
what you are suggesting?!
To doubt the High Seeker is...
[Cassandra sighs]
[Byron] This elf girl
supposedly has the ability
to control wild beasts.
That's why the
Blood Mages wanted her.
[Cassandra]
That's a rare power,
but what does it have to
do with the conspiracy?
I don't know yet.
But I'm convinced
she's the key to all of it.
[Cassandra] And because
the High Seeker refused
to return her to the Circle,
you think that means...?
[Byron] I'm not sure what
to think about any of it!
For now, I'm taking Avexis
to a friend I know I can trust.
Who? Tell me!
[Byron and Cassandra gasp]
[birds caw]
Are these the friends
you were waiting for?
[Byron] We can't take on these
numbers and protect the girl.
We must retreat.
[Cassandra] Go!
Cassandra, wait!
[Cassandra pants]
[Blood Mage] Hya!
[Cassandra grunts]
[Frenic sneers]
[Cassandra and
Blood Mages grunt]
[Byron and Blood Mages grunt]
[Cassandra struggles]
[Byron] Behind you!
Byron!
[Byron wheezes]
[Frenic] I'll be taking
what is mine, Seeker.
[Byron] No... Avexis...
[Cassandra and Blood Mage grunt]
[Cassandra yells]
[Cassandra] Release her! Now!
[Blood Mage] Seeker
reinforcements are approaching.
[Frenic groans]
[Frenic] Your comrades are
too late, Dragon Hunter...
[Frenic] This round...
belongs to me...
[Cassandra gasps]
Byron!
[Byron grunts in pain]
Go after them...
We must get Avexis back...
The Chantry is in peril...
I should have listened to you...
Cassandra...
Hate can only breed more hate...
[Cassandra shudders]
Byron!
[footstep]
[Cassandra and Galyan pant]
[Cassandra and Galyan grunt]
Filthy murdering Mage!
I‐I'm not the one you want!
[Cassandra yells]
[Galyan trembles]
[Cassandra] Where did your
accomplices take Avexis?!
Stop! You have the wrong person!
Silence, Blood Mage!
[Galyan yelps]
[Galyan] No, I'm a Circle Mage,
not a Blood Mage!
A Mage is a Mage!
[Galyan breathes]
[Seeker A] There they are!
Stand down! Lower your
weapon, Cassandra!
[Seeker A] You have
some explaining to do.
[Seeker C] He's dead!
[Seeker A]
What?! What happened here? Talk!
These Blood Mages killed Byron.
I'm telling you, I had no
part in this, I swear it!
[Seeker B2] Where's the girl?
They took her.
[Seeker A] Or perhaps
you gave her to them!
Why did you and Byron
remove her from her guard?
Talk, Cassandra!
[Seeker A] So be it.
Take her into custody!
And the Mage as well!
What?!
Listen, we have to get Avexis
back as soon as possible.
The Chantry's in danger!
[Seeker A] You had your chance.
Save it for the High Seeker.
Byron came here to meet me.
I promised him that I'd
take Avexis to a safe place.
There's no way
those Blood Mages
could've known to follow
you here tonight.
Not without spies on the inside.
Byron suspected that
someone within the Chantry
is behind a conspiracy.
If he was right, and we let
these Seekers take us back,
there's a good chance
we will be "silenced."
Shut up, Mage!
[Seeker A] There a problem?
[Seeker A]
Keep it down back there.
Circle Mages have pledged
their allegiance to the Chantry.
It's Blood Mages
who are the opposition.
Please don't assume
I'm one of them,
but I can find out
where they are.
You said yourself that if
we don't get Avexis back,
something terrible will happen.
And Byron will have then
lost his life for nothing.
Are you sure you know
a way to find Avexis?
Byron risked defying
our Order to protect her.
It seems that if I am
to discover the truth,
I will have to do the same.
This man has a knife!
What?!
[Seekers]
‐‐Hm?
‐‐What's going on over there?
We told you to surrender your
weapons, Mage. Where is it?!
No sudden moves! Search him!
[Cassandra and Seekers grunt]
[Seeker yells]
[Galyan] Impressive...
[Galyan yelps]
[Galyan grunts]
Wait! They aren't pursuing us.
You're pathetic!
[Galyan cries out]
[Cassandra] Whoa!
[Cassandra and Galyan grunt]
Get off of me!
Prefer the top, do you?
[Galyan] Ah! Ah...
[Cassandra] Shut up!
[Galyan breathes lightly]
[Galyan] No! Wait!
[Cassandra grunts]
If you were of no use to me, I'd
cut you down here and now, Mage.
But I forget my manners.
Here I've rolled in the bushes
with a pretty young lady
and I haven't
introduced myself.
I am Regalyan d'Marcall.
My friends call me Galyan.
[Cassandra] Well, "friend"...
If you value your life,
you will take me to the Blood
Mage that murdered Byron.
[Galyan inhales anxiously]
[High Seeker] That is all we
know at this time, Most Holy.
This is unbelievable...
A traitor amongst the Seekers?
We are currently reviewing
all the facts, Your Reverence.
It's unthinkable!
The Seekers are the
most pure among us,
yet two of your own have
betrayed the Chantry.
A Seeker would never
go against the Chantry.
I assure you that their
actions can be explained.
[Knight Commander]
I have a company of knights
standing at the ready.
Permission to pursue the
traitors at once, Your Eminence.
Perhaps the Seekers
would be hesitant
to hunt down one of their own.
Dispatch your
Templars immediately.
These renegades must
be brought to justice.
[Knight Commander laughs softly]
[Galyan] There.
Is this the Blood Mage hideout?
No, that's a Circle safe house.
[Cassandra] A trap?!
Will you quit waving
that thing around?
My intelligence‐gathering
associates meet here.
If anyone can find where
the Blood Mages are, they can.
More Mages just
mean more trouble!
You expect me to trust you?!
[Galyan sighs]
Well, Byron trusted me!
Byron and I were friends.
I was the one who told him
where the Blood Mage
ceremony would be held.
[Galyan] The First
Enchanter sent me
to investigate suspicious
Blood Mage activities.
It's thanks to the
intelligence we gathered
that Byron was able
to rescue Avexis.
However, the plan fell apart
when the High Seeker did
not return her to the Circle.
I'm not sure the
reason behind it,
but that was when
Byron started to question
the High Seeker's
true intentions.
So Byron brought Avexis
into the forest tonight
to give her to you...
Yes. She is a
uniquely gifted girl.
That's why I think the
Blood Mages abducted her.
Byron and I planned on
hiding her here to keep her safe
until we could get to the
bottom of the conspiracy.
[Galyan] What?
The horses are uneasy.
[Cassandra gasps]
[Galyan] By the Maker...
[Cassandra] You knew these men?
Loki...
[Haydi coughs, wheezes]
Haydi!
[Galyan] What happened?
Who did this?!
Blood Mages...
They caught us just as we
returned from Lazarro's...
[Haydi exhales harshly]
Haydi!
[Galyan] Be at peace,
my friend...
[Cassandra] Who's Lazarro?
An information trader
from a village just
outside of Montfort.
He's the one who told me
about the dragon ceremony.
Take me to him.
We'll find out
everything he knows!
The Blood Mages may already
be waiting for us, you know.
[Galyan] They've been one
step ahead of us this far.
[Cassandra shouts] Hyah!
[Cassandra] Be ready.
[Cassandra] You work close
to the edge of Chantry law,
but still claim you are
loyal to the Circle?
[Galyan] Contrary
to common belief,
not all Mages wish to see
the Chantry deposed.
Those of us within the Circle
seek only to be treated with
equal dignity and respect.
I do my part to help ensure our
efforts are not undermined
by the actions of a few.
[Cassandra]
So you formed a network
to keep tabs on rogue Mages?
[Galyan] Apostates
like those in this blood
cult we're dealing with
might claim to act in
the cause of freedom,
but more often their only aim
is seizing power for themselves.
[Cassandra] I'd think it
would benefit the Circle
to have Mages in power.
[Galyan] Not like these. That
wouldn't be good for anyone.
[footsteps running]
[Seeker] Search teams one
and two have reported in.
There's been no
sign of Cassandra
or the Mage in the
Igrecia Forest, sir.
[First Enchanter] Has there
been any word from Galyan?
[Alte]
I'm afraid not, First Enchanter.
[First Enchanter]
We must find him
before the Seekers
or Templars do...
[Alte] Understood. I will take
charge of the search myself.
I leave it to you, then.
[First Enchanter]
I only pray we are not too late.
[Galyan]
You can't see it from here,
but Lazarro's house is
halfway up this cliff.
He's an elf recluse.
Half‐mad, but he hears things.
No one knows how.
He's also quite paranoid.
How can we get in?
Well, you could always try
asking to send down a ladder.
Lazarro!
It's me, Galyan!
Lazarro! Are you there?
[Lazarro screams]
[Lazarro and Cassandra grunt]
Lazarro, calm down!
We just need some information!
[Lazarro shudders]
If you cooperate and
tell us what you know,
I'll let you keep
your filthy head!
I know nothing!
I'm not involved!
Cassandra! Please...
[Lazarro whimpers softly]
Where's the girl?
What? What girl?
Perhaps you can't hear well.
Let me clear your ears for you.
[Lazarro screams]
Frenic! Frenic has her!
Who's Frenic?
[Lazarro] The leader
of the Blood Mages.
He needs her...
Needs her power!
For what? What is
he planning to do?!
[Lazarro] Attack...
T‐Ten Year...
Frenic is going to attack
the Ten Year Gathering?
Who is his accomplice
in the Chantry?
Someone high up...!
What's their name?
‐‐I don't know!
‐‐Who is it?! Talk!
[Lazarro screams]
[Cassandra] I am only going
to ask you one more time.
Give me the name. Now!
[Galyan] No, you don't!
This is a vial of
Nesium Suspension.
It emits a bright flash
when shattered.
So you think you can escape
using mere parlor tricks?!
They'll kill me!
"They"? You mean
the Blood Mages?
I was to alert them
if you showed up!
Sorry, we can't let you do that.
It's too late.
[rumbling and creaking]
[Cassandra] What is that?
[Galyan] I'm not
sure I want to know...
[Ogre roars]
[Lazarro whimpers]
[Lazarro screams]
[Ogre roars]
[Cassandra] Hya!
[Galyan and Cassandra cough]
[Galyan] You all right?
[Cassandra] Of course I am.
[Galyan chuckles]
[Ogres and Golems growl]
Oh, sod!
[Galyan] The eyes... Their
minds are being controlled.
[Ogre roars]
[Cassandra yells repeatedly]
[Ogre screams]
There's too many!
[Ogre roars]
[Galyan] Yah!
Not good...
Thanks, Lazarro.
Now... let's just hope
this is actually more
than a parlor trick!
[indistinct roars,
gradually dying away]
I should be able
to handle this pain!
We need to get to a safe place
where I can treat your wound.
I don't need your magic...!
Are you all right?
Sorry...
It's hard for me to admit
I'm in your debt, Mage.
My name isn't "Mage."
It's Galyan.
[Knight Commander]
There they are!
[Cassandra and Galyan gasp]
Why are you here?!
Hm.
After them!
Arrest those traitors!
[Templars] Whoa!
[Knight Commander]
Get up! Don't let them escape!
[Cassandra and Galyan
struggle and pant]
[Galyan] Oh, my.
[sound of horses approaching]
[Knight Commander]
There's nowhere to run!
Now surrender. Nice and easy.
[Galyan] It seems we're
out of options here...
[Cassandra] Not entirely...
We can make it.
[Galyan shudders]
Don't be a fool.
You'll never survive the jump.
That's for the Maker to decide.
Not a Templar!
[Cassandra] Get ready.
Don't I get a say in this?
[Cassandra grunts]
[Galyan screams]
[distant splash]
[Knight Commander sneers]
[Galyan coughs]
[Galyan] If I hadn't been here,
you would have been fish food.
[footsteps]
Preparations for the
Ten Year Gathering
are proceeding without delay.
[Divine] You have done
a superb job, as always.
I shudder to think
what I would do without
your selfless service.
You need never worry about that.
Since the day I entered
the Chantry as a girl,
I have wished only to be
the Right Hand of the Divine.
And that you are.
More than I could ever ask.
[Grand Cleric] It will be a
great day for the Chantry,
the Maker willing.
[Divine] No matter
what happens,
we must continue
with the ceremony.
The Knight Commander
has assured me
the Templars can
handle Chantry security.
[Galyan]
Come on. Just a little farther.
We can rest here for a while.
[Galyan]
Now then... Let there be light.
[crackling fire]
[Cassandra breathes heavily]
[approaching steps]
Cassandra, please...
let me treat your wound.
[Galyan]
Ah, that is a nasty scrape.
Fortunately...
I happen to have
just the thing for it.
Now this will hurt a bit.
[Galyan]
Sorry.
[Cassandra gasps in pain]
My battle magic is mediocre,
but I am excellent
at healing spells.
[Galyan gasps]
[Galyan] You should be able to
move it normally in a day or so.
[Cassandra] My elder brother
knew all about healing herbs.
[Galyan]
Ah. Was he a Mage?
[Cassandra snorts]
It's merely a jest.
He was murdered by Mages.
Blood Mages...
When I was a child,
my brother was cut down
right in front of me...
They needed fresh dragon
blood for their rituals...
So they came looking for
the legendary dragon‐hunting
families of Nevarra,
to capture a dragon for them.
[people screaming]
[horses galloping]
[Cassandra] My brother
was the best in our family.
His skills and honor
were unmatched.
He wouldn't sacrifice a dragon
for their corrupted magic.
The Blood Mages killed
all those who refused them.
[metal clanging together]
[grunt of pain]
Uncle!!
[Young Cassandra takes
short, gaspy breaths]
[Cassandra's Brother
pants heavily]
[horse's galloping hooves]
Anthony...!
[slow‐motion panting]
[sound of scythe
against the air]
[crackling fire]
My brother was strong... kind...
and I loved him dearly...
I've hated Mages ever since...
Blood or Circle Mages...
They all seemed the same to me.
No different from the Mage
who murdered my brother...
I'm so sorry, Cassandra.
It is true that both Circle
and Blood Mages are Mages...
Our methods may differ,
but there is no denying
we practice a common art...
And as a Mage, I would
like to express my sorrow.
What happened to your brother
was truly something horrendous.
[crackling fire]
[crickets' chirping]
[quiet rustling of armor]
[Templar A]
Move in.
They're gone!
[Knight Commander]
They couldn't have gotten far.
Find them!
[All Templars] Sir!
[horse whickering]
[retreating hooves]
Cassandra and the Mage
have disappeared, Frenic...
They must be eliminated before
the Ten Year Gathering‐‐ Oh!
You were saying, Commander?
[Galyan]
What have we here?
This is an Elven Stone. He was
sending a message to someone.
[Galyan]
"Understood, Knight Commander.
I will commence the search
for Cassandra and Galyan's
whereabouts immediately.
Frenic."
So, then... you are
in league with Frenic.
That's how you
found us so quickly!
You'll pay for your
betrayal of the Chantry!
[Knight Commander chuckles]
[Cassandra gasps in pain]
The wound still hurts,
doesn't it, Cassandra?
You both know too much...
[metal clanging together]
[Cassandra cries out in pain]
[Cassandra pants]
[Galyan pants]
[Cassandra]
Filthy traitor...
Byron is dead because of you...
[Cassandra grunts in anger]
[Cassandra cries out in pain]
[Cassandra]
No! This is not finished!
[Galyan] Cassandra, protecting
the Circle and Chantry
is more important than revenge.
[Cassandra]
I owe it to Byron!
[Galyan] We must show this
stone to the Chantry at once!
Cassandra!
[chanting]
[Frenic]
The conversion is complete...
[Frenic] Behold!
The terror we shall soon
unleash upon the Chantry!
Now Avexis... Make them fly!
[deep growling sounds]
[Frenic] Let our cries for
vengeance be carried forth
on wings of fire...
[satisfied sigh]
Good...
[loud roar]
[Cassandra pants and grunts]
[swishing, thwacking noises]
[Galyan]
Go now. Safe journey, my friend.
[wings flapping]
[Cassandra]
This is it!
[creaking, groaning noise]
[Cassandra]
Give me a hand.
[creaking, groaning noise]
[metallic slamming sound]
The High Seeker's Office
is through here.
And you're sure that the front
door is out of the question?
[Cassandra]
Just come on.
[Galyan] Suddenly I get the
sense that sneaking in like this
isn't going to help our case...
[muffled coughing]
[High Seeker]
I rather liked that cabinet.
[Cassandra]
High Seeker?
I've been waiting for
your report, Cassandra...
I feared you were captured.
Feared? I thought
you were hunting me.
I assumed you had your reasons
and that you would
report in eventually.
[High Seeker]
So...?
Where do I start...?
[High Seeker] Hm...
While the Knight Commander
and I have had our differences,
I can't believe that
he would go so far
as to subvert the Chantry.
Then perhaps you
should look at this.
[Galyan]
It's evidence of our claims.
Interesting...
I must show this to
the Divine at once.
So you believe me?
You've risked your life and
honor in pursuit of the truth.
How could I doubt?
You have the heart of a
true Seeker, Cassandra...
As did Byron.
[Cassandra]
Thank you, Sir...
[High Seeker]
Wait here until my return.
[Cassandra] But there is
still so much to be done...
Leave this to me...
and get some rest, Cassandra.
Yes, High Seeker.
[sound of impact]
[footsteps]
[pained grunts]
[Cassandra gasps]
[wrenching sound]
[Cassandra]
High Seeker!
You...!
Isn't this yours?
You left it in the cave.
Allow me to return it.
Seekers!
[armor clanking]
[running footsteps]
[Seeker A]
High Seeker...!
[Seeker B]
My liege!
The fugitives murdered
the High Seeker. Arrest them!
‐‐[Cassandra] No!
‐‐[Seeker A] Hold her!
‐‐[Seeker B] Silence, traitor!
‐‐[Cassandra] He's lying!
[Cassandra]
It was him!
He's the murderer!
[organ music]
Confess before the Maker
and be absolved of your sins.
I just murdered the High Seeker
and framed Cassandra
and the fugitive Mage.
They have been
branded as traitors.
And soon, they will be
executed for their crimes.
[Grand Cleric takes short,
trembling breaths]
[Grand Cleric sighs quietly]
Frenic and the girl are ready.
A new era is upon us.
The day where you may be
called "Divine" is imminent.
[satisfied grunt]
And once the plan
comes to fruition,
I will personally ensure
that Frenic's mouth is sealed.
Pitiful Blood Mage...
I am looking forward
to the Ten Year Gathering.
[murmuring crowd]
[Divine] I don't understand it.
He was such a great man.
Why would Cassandra do this?
One can never fathom the
purpose of evil, Your Grace...
But rest assured, they will
get their just reward.
All of Orlais shares
your pain, Most Holy,
but in your own words,
we must proceed with
the Ten Year Gathering.
The Grand Clerics
have assembled,
and the congregation has
gathered in the courtyard.
They eagerly
await your blessing.
I fear that great evil
has gathered
amongst the good today...
Pray that the Maker
can bring us all together.
Byron and the High Seeker
believed in me...
and now they're dead.
I should've let you finish
the Knight Commander
when we had the chance.
[approaching footsteps]
Well, well, well...
[Knight Commander chuckles]
[Knight Commander] After
all your efforts,
in the end, it came to this...
You've landed your heads
on the chopping block,
and we still have Avexis.
What are you doing with her?
[Knight Commander laughs]
You mean you don't know?
The whole point of Frenic's
blood ritual was to give him
complete control of
the girl and her abilities.
Control her for what purpose?
Frenic will use her powers to
summon dragons to the Chantry...
They should be
en route any moment.
Is that even possible...?
You're going after the Divine?!
Yes, then a new era will unfold!
A new era where we rule...
Even if you succeed in
murdering the Divine,
the Seekers will never
let you seize power!
Oh, really?
You're right, they wouldn't...
Not him, at least.
But a Cleric...?
There's a reason
they've chosen dragons
to carry out their
assassination plot.
The Divine and
all the candidates next
in line to succeed her
are attending the
Ten Year Gathering,
and they will all be wiped out.
This will be done publicly as
if it were a natural disaster,
and whoever is left standing
will be the next Divine.
But who is it? Who's the
traitor amongst the clerics?!
I have no time to participate
in wild speculations
with the likes of you.
Who is the traitor...?! Who?!
My orders are to execute you
before the start
of the Gathering.
You'll have to continue
this conversation
with Byron and the High Seeker.
[Knight Commander sneers]
Who?! Who is the traitor?!
Templars!
Prepare for the execution!
[Cassandra]
Tell me! Come back here!
[Cassandra cries
out in frustration]
[crowd murmuring]
Yes, take it all in, Avexis...
We are witness to the final
moments of a dying age...
And you shall bring
about its demise.
[crowd cheers and whistles]
[distant cheering]
Oh, Maker above!
Shine down your
light and save me!
[Templar A]
Silence, prisoner.
[Knight Commander]
Wait!
[Knight Commander] I'll dispatch
this fallen Seeker myself.
Hmph. Your bravery
is commendable...
Ahhhh!
[various attack cries]
[Cassandra]
Galyan!
Are you all right?
Galyan.. We got your message...
Sorry we had
to cut things so close!
I sent a message with a
bird to the Circle of Magi...
Thank the Maker it arrived...
[Templars growling angrily]
[Cassandra shouts]
[Alte] After you were
captured, we trailed
the Knight Commander
and learned some very
interesting information...
He has been conspiring
with the Grand Cleric of Orlais.
The Grand Cleric?!
Yes. They have been
meeting secretly for months.
[Knight Commander]
Hyaargh!
Cassandra!
I know about the Grand Cleric.
You have both turned
your backs on the Chantry!
Ha! On the contrary,
we are ushering in a
new era for the Chantry...
One where events like
Kirkwall will not be tolerated!
[Cassandra] We won't
allow your plan to succeed!
[Cassandra and
Knight Commander struggle]
Knight Commander grunt]
[Knight Commander
grunts in pain]
"Hate can only breed more hate."
Those were Byron's
last words to me.
Cassandra...
[Cassandra] Tie him up.
He will answer for his crimes.
[Circle Mage A]
You heard her. Up!
In the end, it came to this...
[bells tolling in the distance]
[Galyan]
It's the start of the Gathering.
[Divine] Citizens of Orlais,
honored faithful
from lands beyond,
today we gather
to honor the Maker
and his greatest gift to us...
...his wife of the spirit,
Andraste, our beloved prophet
who gave her life so that
the Chantry might live...
This day, each decade, marks
the beginning of a new life.
A day when the
Maker's benediction
brings great joy and...
[rushing air]
[crowd murmurs in alarm]
[cries and screams
from crowd below]
[Divine gasps]
[clerics give out
frightened cries]
[dragon roars]
Go on! Good! Crush them all!
[screams from clerics]
[loud roar]
[screaming, frantic
cries of the clerics]
Maker's wrath! He sends
dragons to punish our sins!
[crowd cries in panic]
[Templar A]
Protect the Divine!
[Templar B]
Come on!
[Templar H]
Most Holy...
No... She's cut off...
[Cassandra]
We're too late...
Frenic and Avexis
should be close by!
[Galyan]
I'll find them!
[pained roaring]
[Cassandra yells]
[dragon cries out in pain]
[pained, gradually
weakening roars]
[dragon growls]
[crowd cheers]
[Frenic] Dragon Hunter...
Call the High Dragon!
[commotion of crowd]
[High Dragon roars]
Finish her! Yes! Yes!! Hahahaha!
[Galyan] She's done enough
of your bidding, Frenic.
You'll never
harm this girl again!
It's over. All of it.
[High Dragon roars]
[Grand Cleric pants]
[Cassandra grunts]
[roar of pain]
[High Dragon roars]
No... No!!
[Grand Cleric gasps]
[quiet growling]
[Cassandra] Are you
all right, your grace?
[Templar H]
Your Holiness!
[Templars struggle]
[Templar H]
Most Holy!
[Cassandra]
Quickly. Help her down.
‐‐[Templar I] Your Holiness!
‐‐[Te. H] Right, we've got her.
Thank you, Cassandra...
Come, Your Holiness.
[Templar I]
The Maker be with you!
Heh, heh, heh...
[Frenic] Fool...
Do you really think I will
surrender so easily?
[Frenic yells]
[Frenic]
Hyargh!
[Alte]
Together, men!
[Grand Cleric]
Frenic...
[Cassandra] There is no
one coming to help you.
The Knight Commander is dead.
Do you hear?
Your plan failed, Mage.
[Grand Cleric grunts in pain]
[stabbing noise]
[dripping sounds]
You are no longer
of any use to me!
[Frenic]
This was never about her.
I merely exploited her ambition
as a means to free us
from the oppressive
binds of the Chantry,
and create a new world
controlled by Mages!
[Frenic] As a fellow Mage,
you should understand.
You and I are not the same.
Then I will destroy you all,
along with the Chantry!
[Frenic] Hwa!
[Frenic struggles]
Eh... heh heh heh...
Yaaa!
[ripping, crunching sounds]
[deep growl from Frenic]
[loud roar]
[Alte]
Now, men! Everything you've got!
[Alte gasps]
[Cassandra pants]
Avexis! Wake up! Avexis! Please!
We need you, Avexis! Wake up!
[Frenic roars]
Aaaaagh!
[Cassandra yelps in pain]
[Frenic roars]
[High Dragon roars]
[Galyan]
Thank you, Avexis...
[both creatures roar]
[High Dragon roars]
Come on!
[pained roars]
[quiet growls]
[pained roar]
The righteous stand
before the darkness
and the Maker shall
guide their hands.
Cassandra...!
[Frenic roars loudly in pain]
[commotion of crowd]
For the Chantry!
[Crowd]
[Templars]
For the Chantry!
Yeah!
[crowd cheering and whistling]
What do you think...?
Not bad, huh?
[Cassandra chuckles]
Cassandra...
You are the bravest
person I have ever met,
and the most beautiful....
This isn't the
time or the place!
[Galyan laughs]
[Cassandra]
You fool.
Galyan, you've helped me win
back more than just my honor.
Suddenly, the world
is different for me now.
[Cassandra]
Thank you, for everything.
[cheering crowd]
[Avexis giggles]
For risking her life to
protect the Chantry
against the darkest of evil,
I hereby proclaim Cassandra
Pentaghast the Hero of Orlais.
[cheers rise from the crowd]
[Divine] And the
Chantry also wishes
to express its appreciation...
of the heroic Mage that fought
beside her, Regalyan d'Marcall.
[cheers rise from the crowd]
And for upholding the
highest standards
of the Order of Seekers
and demonstrating
unwavering faith to the Chantry,
Cassandra Pentaghast
shall from this day forward
be the Right Hand
of the Divine.
[cheers rise from the crowd]
[Divine]
Come forth, child.
[wild cheers from the crowd]
[organ music]
[doors opening and shutting]
Your Holiness...
Cassandra...
You seem troubled.
This attack...
It is only the beginning.
There is a storm coming, child.
We must be prepared.
How may I serve?
♪ closing music ♪