Rudy.
[ROXY]
A list of the dead. Please, no.
Good. Rudy and his family
aren't on it. Thank God.
[gasps]
[TALHAND]
Well color me surprised,
Fittoa gets wiped off the map
but that tough ol'
bastard soldiers on.
Please, Paul's lived
through worse than this.
If we were lucky,
he would've been
sent to another world.
I'm sorry, but do you
know Paul Greyrat?
‐‐Who's asking?
‐‐Who are you?
[PAUL]
Dear Rudeus.
Zenith, Lilia, and Aisha
are all missing.
Norn is safe with me.
I don't know where you are,
or who you're with,
but I know you can
find your way home,
even if you're traveling alone.
So I'm going to look
for you last, my son.
I'm headed to the
Millis Continent.
It's where your mother
was born and raised,
and her family is still there.
I've sent a message
to Lilia's family as well.
I want you to search
the northern part
of the Central Continent.
Send word if you
find any of them.
Zenith, Lilia:
please do the same.
Now. To anyone
who knows my family,
and to former members of
The Fangs of the Black Wolf:
I need your help.
I'm sure some of you
don't think too highly of me.
I won't beg for
your forgiveness.
You can insult me all you want.
If you ask me to lick
your boots, I'll do it.
My fortune's gone,
so I can't offer
a reward, but please.
Help me find my family.
Send all correspondence to
the Millishion
Adventurers' Guild,
Holy Millis Kingdom,
Millis Continent.
Party: Buena Villager
Search Party.
Clan: Fittoa Domain Search Team.
Paul Greyrat.
[RUDEUS]
Our job is to investigate
a mysterious monster
in the Petrified Forest.
We get five scrap‐iron
pieces for finding it,
and two iron pieces
if we slay it.
It's a great deal.
[ERIS]
What kind of monster is it?
[RUDEUS] Big and slithery,
but that's all we know.
[ERIS]
Is it gonna be strong?
Yeah, if I had to guess.
Awesome, I can't
wait to meet it!
[RUDEUS] Whatever it is,
I'm sure we can take it.
And then we can kiss
our financial woes
goodbye for a while.
Hey. Someone beat us here.
[RUDEUS]
Crap, he's from the Guild, too.
[RUDEUS clears throat]
[KURT sighs]
[BLAZE laughs]
What was that about?
It looks like we're all here
to do the same job,
more or less.
Should we go?
No, of course not.
'Cause now it's a race.
Let's go, then!
Hurry it up, slowpokes!
Wait. I'm worried
about those children.
We should follow them.
I dunno, if we stick
too close to them,
they might figure out
you really are a Superd.
So what?
You realize it'll be a
disaster if word gets out?
Would you rather I stand back
and watch them die?
That's not what I'm saying.
We can tail them,
but we shouldn't jump in
to help unless they're
in real danger.
[ERIS groans] Come on,
I thought I'd get to
fight something
strong for once! Ugh!
They're far too careless.
Do they not understand
that they're
completely surrounded
by monsters?
Well...
[ALL gasp]
‐‐Not yet!
‐‐Why not?
Let's see how they handle this.
[speaking in a foreign language]
I'm going!
No! One more minute.
[RUDEUS]
I want 'em on the ropes.
Our reputation will
get a bigger boost
if we swoop in at
the last minute.
We'll let 'em get
knocked around a little,
then save the day and
I'll heal them with magic.
It's not just perfect.
It's genius.
[KURT panting]
[RUIJERD]
Why did you stop me?
I could have saved him.
I thought that waiting
would benefit us the most.
[RUDEUS gasps]
You were willing to
let a child die
for your own self‐interest?
You can't be serious!
I'm sorry. But I'm
trying my hardest, okay?
[gasps]
[KURT crying]
Hey, good luck out there!
[roaring]
Is that another snake?
Yes.
[BLAZE screams]
That's a Red‐Hood Cobra.
I wouldn't have expected
to find one here.
Then that's our mysterious
monster, I take it.
[RUIJERD]
It seems so.
That's a powerful enemy.
I doubt his party
ever stood a chance.
He'll die if we
don't do something!
Come on, what's the plan?
Can we win?
Definitely.
Then what are we waiting for?
[ERIS yells]
[gasps]
[roars]
Again?
Eris!
[ERIS yells]
Rudeus!
Right!
Did we win?
Yes! We did it!
[RUDEUS]
Sure did.
[ERIS laughs]
We did it!
[RUDEUS] I don't know what we
would have done without you.
[RUIJERD]
We were too late.
Huh?
[RUDEUS]
Bastard.
[RUDEUS] Every plan
I've had since we got here
has totally backfired.
So what now?
We could go ahead
and cough up the money,
then escape after that.
But even if we got away,
he could get our
licenses revoked
before we make it
to the next city.
That's too risky.
Maybe we can scapegoat
Jalil and Vizquel and play dumb?
No, that ship has sailed.
Just thinking about it
is exhausting.
Ugh, focus. There has
to be another way out.
Rudeus?
We're gonna be fine.
Leave everything to me.
[RUDEUS]
Remember the goal.
I have to get Eris home safe,
no matter what.
For her, I'll flood
this whole city.
[RUDEUS]
We're leaving.
Even if we have to
betray Ruijerd.
[gasps]
[STREET screaming]
[NOKOPARA screams]
Huh? What the hell?
Ruijerd, wait!
Please don't kill him!
[RUDEUS gasps]
Where are you going?!
[RUDEUS]
Ruijerd!
[ERIS]
‐‐Where are you?
‐‐Come on, where'd you go?
[RUDEUS] Will you please
say something?
[RUIJERD]
Sorry.
[RUDEUS] For what? I should
be apologizing to you.
I was too focused on
finding the easy way out.
I just wanted to make money
and make us look good.
I'm sorry. I've been acting
like a selfish idiot.
No you haven't.
Even the best‐laid battle plans
can go awry sometimes.
It's not your fault.
I didn't always
understand your motives
or abide by your decisions.
But now, I see that
I misjudged you.
In town, you were prepared
to kill to survive.
I could sense your resolve.
There's no shame
in being desperate
to try to protect something.
[ERIS]
Hm?
You've proven yourself
to be a fine warrior, Rudeus.
But I've treated you
like a child.
What does that word
even mean to you, Ruijerd?
"Warrior."
Being a warrior is
a matter of pride.
We fight to defend the weak
as well as our comrades.
That's in my blood.
I will stay at your side.
And you owe me nothing
in return for that.
So, don't worry about
the Superd's reputation.
Protect what you must,
no matter the cost.
No matter...
I will. Thank you
for everything.
[RUDEUS]
But I will restore your name
if it's the last thing I do.
Did you listen to
anything I said?
Am I that untrustworthy to you?
Of course not, I want to
repay you because I trust you.
You're certainly
a stubborn one.
Yeah, I think I
picked that up from you.
[BOTH chuckling]
[BOTH laughing]
Well?
Yeah.
[RUDEUS] I'm no warrior.
Never have been.
And to be honest,
I'm not sure I'll ever have
the sense of pride
Ruijerd does, either.
But in that moment,
his approval of me
made me feel... happy.
Like an equal.
[ERIS]
I'll take care of both of you!
[ALL laughing]
Wh‐What did you do to your head?
I shaved it.
What happened yesterday
made it clear that
my hair frightens people
above all else.
‐‐I see.
‐‐That's a great look for you!
[RUDEUS]
Really?
Oh! Hang on a sec!
Uh‐‐
[RUDEUS]
Coulda sworn it was... Got it!
[BOTH]
Hm?
[RUDEUS] Might as well hide your
third eye while we're at it.
[ERIS]
Hey, look! Now we match!
Yes.
[RUDEUS]
Up to this point,
I've been desperate to figure
out everything on my own.
I was too controlling, and that
contributed to my failures.
We'll run into all sorts
of problems down the road.
So I'd like for us to
talk them out together
and find solutions as a group.
Fewer surprises that way,
and hopefully, fewer fights.
Sound good?
Aye.
Works for me!
All right, then, team.
I hereby call the first‐ever
Dead End strategy
meeting to order.
Destination, the Asura Kingdom!