[PAUL]
I'm so sorry. Rudy!
Oh, Father.
[RUDEUS] I'm sorry, too.
For everything.
I think I know what
we're having for dinner!
Hail and well met,
fair travelers,
I am Rodriguez, third student of
Auber the Peacock Blade!
He, in turn, pupil to the
famous North God Kalman!
I can see from your bearing
that you are a man
of great renown!
I wish to request a bout!
I haven't sparred
like this in some time.
You have bested me!
I marvel at your
strength, good sir!
In all my travels,
never have I met your match!
Fare thee well,
great warrior of the Superd!
I hope for yet another bout
when next we meet!
Hail and well met!
Hail and well met, sir!
[ERIS retches]
Rudeus, stop standing around
and heal me already.
[RUDEUS retching]
Let this divine power
be rich and nourishing--
How're you holding up, Ruijerd?
Are you okay?
I'm perfectly well,
and have no idea
why you two have fallen ill.
Oh cool, rub it in. But hey--
[RUDEUS] I'm glad you get
to be up here with us,
instead of having
to stow away again.
It turns out, my father is
good for something
after all, huh?
[RUIJERD] Try not to speak
too poorly of the man.
[chuckles] I promise you
he doesn't care.
Our relationship is
built on jabs like that.
I'll take your word.
[RUDEUS] Gotta say,
it's a relief to make it back
to the Central Continent.
It's taken forever.
Though I guess this is
only another turning point.
Yes, we've still got
a long road ahead of us.
[RUDEUS]
Good news, though.
The captain told me
that the kingdom
we're set to travel through
is the biggest rice producer
in all the human territories.
[RUIJERD]
Oh? Are you fond of rice?
More than I can possibly say.
Not to brag or anything,
but I've been known
to put away bowl after bowl
and still have room
to kill a few rice balls
when I'm done.
How can you possibly
think about food
at a time like this, you weirdo?
If you feel good enough
to chitchat,
you feel good enough
to cast Healing--
[ERIS retching]
And the roads on
the Central Continent
should be pretty
well-maintained,
so I'd like to make
a point to enjoy
our journey moving forward.
Oh! But our families
and building up
the Superd's reputation will
still take priority, of course.
Sound good?
Yes, sounds good. No objections.
[RUDEUS] So, Zenith, Lilia,
little Aisha, and Sylphie
are all still
out there somewhere.
No news about any of 'em.
Heck, we don't even know
if Ghislaine's alive.
Maybe by the time
we get back to Fittoa,
everyone will there be waiting
for us, safe and sound.
And maybe that's too optimistic,
but tearing my
hair out with worry
won't do us any good, either.
[RUDEUS]
So why not think happy thoughts?
For better or worse, the Millis
Continent is behind us.
We'll cross the
King Dragon Realm next,
and after that, Shirone.
[RUDEUS] I'll finally
get to see Roxy again.
[RUDEUS retches]
[ROXY]
Wow. How did Blaze die?
Eaten. By Red-Hood Cobra,
if the story is true.
[ROXY]
He was never exactly nice to me.
That foul mouth used to
curse up a storm
any time I stepped out of line.
And I remember
the constant fighting
drove Hawkendale insane.
And yet, we made a great party.
[NOKOPARA] Well, cheers to
being a support class.
Might not have made it to
middle age, otherwise, eh?
You've really changed
over the years, Roxy.
Do you think I have?
It's kinda hard for me to tell.
Oh, yeah! For starters, you've
gotten a lot more mature.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you making fun
of me or something?
I'm not making fun of you!
I just mean your aura's changed.
You used to come off as
more of a kid, you know?
I've put a lot of years
behind me since then,
even if it doesn't
look that way.
[NOKOPARA] See, that's exactly
what I'm talking about.
'Cause back in the day?
You were constantly
trying to act grown up
and you woulda been
ecstatic if I ever said
you were "mature."
Was I really?
I guess you're right.
I was like that for a long time.
I wanted to prove
I wasn't a child,
and that I should
be taken seriously.
Never mind that I didn't
have any real grasp
on my own skills
or limitations yet.
But these days,
I feel like my reputation
has gotten out of hand.
I know I'm a King-class
water mage,
but people constantly
expect me to do things I can't.
Like silent spellcasting.
You, on the other hand,
haven't changed a bit, though.
Apart from your face.
[NOKOPARA]
Ooh, what're you trying to say?
I'm all old and wrinkly now?
Sure, you could put it that way.
You got a mouth on you now,
don't ya, kiddo?
[ROXY] Well, prove me wrong!
What else changed?
Do you still pick on
new parties for a living?
Hey now, don't make it
sound like extortion,
I'm just teaching them how harsh
the adventuring life
can be for 'em!
That being said,
I've made sure I'm
on my best behavior since I
got burned back in Rikarisu.
You got burned?
How'd you let that happen?
Ah. Party of three
really solid adventurers
calling themselves "Dead End."
[NOKOPARA] But that ain't
a story worth sharin'.
You tell me, though,
as long as you traveled
all the way back out here.
Have you visited
your parents yet?
[gasps]
[NOKOPARA]
Hm?
Oh, uh. I don't think that's...
No, no, no,
you gotta be kidding me.
Don't tell me you haven't been
back to see them
once in all this time?
It's not like they'd be
happy to see me.
So why put myself through that?
Ugh. You're unbelievable.
Okay, I take it all back.
Turns out you haven't
changed one bit
since the last time I saw you.
You're still running away
like a scared little kid.
And why do you think
you should get to
lecture me about any of this?
[NOKOPARA] Well,
I'll have you know that after
you left and
the party dissolved,
I found myself a wife
and we started a family.
I got three little ones now!
And they're so cute,
you wouldn't believe it!
Great. And that matters why?
It matters because
sometimes we fight
like you and your
parents may have,
but at the end of the day,
I would do or be anything
for my family.
And I can guarantee your
folks feel the same way.
[NOKOPARA] Who cares if you
can't use telepathy
like the rest of them, huh?
Some things are more important
than what you can or can't do.
I appreciate the effort,
but I don't think
I need a pep talk
from an obnoxious,
greedy boor like you.
Then this is the last
I'll say about it,
especially 'cuz I know
you won't listen anyway:
but you really should go try
to make up with them
before it's too late.
You've only got
one family, you know?
[ROXY]
I guess it's changed a little.
Bigger. More people.
Maybe a little more greenery.
[ROXY]
But it's still eerily quiet.
Please stop. I can't understand
what you're saying to me.
[ROXY] That's the look
they give outsiders.
[ROXY] I've been a stranger
to my own people
from the day I was born.
Constantly alienated, excluded.
Can't say I missed that.
[ROXY]
I hate this stupid village.
[ROXY] Never thought I'd come
back here of my own free will.
[KIDS giggling]
[thud]
May this divine power offer
the strength to
rise again. Healing.
[pants]
You're not busy, are you?
[ROWIN gasps]
Roxy!
It's been such a long time.
Welcome home, my darling girl!
Have you been all right?
And what have you been doing?
Are you traveling alone?
[ROXY]
I... Um...
We've actually heard a few
stories about you from visitors,
but why don't you
fill us in on the rest?
[ROXY]
It's kind of a lot.
Well, either way,
it's such a relief
to know that you're safe.
Will you stay a while
before you have to leave?
Please, we'd be more
than happy to have you.
Uh, about that.
[gasps]
[ROXY]
I should probably go now.
[ROWIN]
You're leaving so soon?
Yeah.
Roxy, at least stay the night!
[ROXY]
I can't. I have urgent business.
I just wanted to stop by.
Then, when can we expect
to see you again?
[ROXY] I don't know. Honestly.
I might not come back at all.
[ROKARI gasps]
[gasps]
Roxy, dear.
Surely you can visit
every 20 years or so at least.
I'll see what I can do.
Maybe I'll get to stop by
sometime in the next 50 years.
Do you promise?
We'll be waiting!
Okay.
Look at me.
I promised myself I wouldn't cry
if I ever got to see you again.
[ROKARI]
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's okay.
[gasps]
[ROXY laughing]
[ROKARI]
Now, let's see. Ah, here we go.
Looks like this one
is called a "horse."
That's a horse!
[ROKARI]
And this right here is a "pelt."
[ROXY]
Pelt!
That was perfect, Roxy,
you're doing so well!
That's my brilliant girl!
[ROXY]
Can I play with you?
[gasps]
[ROKARI]
Roxy!
[ROXY cries]
Am I a bad girl?
Is that why no one ever
wants to talk to me?
[ROKARI]
No, honey. It's my fault.
I'm so sorry, Roxy.
You're not a bad girl.
[ROXY]
My people don't say anything
truly important
with their mouths.
But I could tell my parents
were heartbroken,
and I knew it was because of me.
Without telepathy,
I would always be an outcast.
[ROXY] That's why I eventually
ran away from home.
I honestly thought they would
all be happier without me.
But maybe...
[crying]
Roxy, what's the matter?
[ROXY]
I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry I left
without saying anything!
[ROXY]
I'm sorry, Dad.
[ROXY] Just maybe.
Words and language have never
been what mattered most.
To any of us.
Oh, look who finally
decided to join us!
Sleep well?
[ROKARI giggles]
Yeah, I guess.
Thanks for asking. Good morning.
[ROWIN] Are you planning
to leave today?
Yeah. I would stay,
but I came out here
to look for some friends
who are missing.
My apprentice is one of them.
I understand.
Wait, now that you mention it,
a boy who said he was
a student of yours
visited about two years ago.
Huh?
Yes, uh. What did he
say his name was?
Rudeus, wasn't it?
That sounds right,
Rudeus Greyrat!
What?
I wonder if those
sweet children have
made it all the way
back home by now.
Hang on, did you say "children"?
You mean he had
somebody else here with him?
Yes, that's right.
He was traveling
with a girl called Eris,
and Mister Ruijerd decided he
would help escort them home.
Oh, Ruijerd is a member
of the Superd tribe.
H-H-H-He-He's a what now?
Yes, we started dealing with him
not too long after you
left the village, actually.
We'd always been
afraid of the Superd,
but he turned out to be quite--
Uh... Roxy?
[ROKARI]
Oh dear!
[ROXY] I'll be sure
to visit again soon.
[ROWIN]
Good.
And feel free to bring
cute little Rudeus
with you next time!
Huh?
Uh-- Absolutely not!
You'll do no such thing!
[ROXY] I just can't wrap
my head around the fact
that Rudeus is traveling
with a Superd.
But if there's
a girl with them, too.
That must mean the infamous trio
calling themselves
"Dead End" is them.
That's the only
viable conclusion.
[sighs]
[ROXY] Everything is finally
starting to make sense.
I thought surely no one
would be foolhardy enough
to impersonate Dead End,
but I wouldn't
put it past Rudeus.
He's fearless.
And if all of that is sanctioned
by the real Dead End?
How amazing will
that boy turn out to be?
Hey. I'm back.
[ELINALISE] I'm sorry, love,
I thought you'd be gone longer!
[ELINALISE moaning]
[ELINALISE]
Uh! Please don't!
[ROXY]
Icicle Break!
[sighs]
[ELINALISE]
That's going to keep happening,
you should get used to it.
[ROXY] Or you could stop
doing it where anyone
could walk in on you
without warning.
Oh, I could, but where's
the fun in that?
I like when people get to watch.
[ROXY sighs]
Hey, where are we off to next?
[ROXY] I think we should
head for the northern shore.
For the time being,
I'd like to focus our efforts
on finding Zenith,
Lilia, and Aisha.
[TALHAND] You don't want to
look for your student?
[ROXY]
Not right now.
I have it on good authority
that he's in safe hands.
I know we'll get to see
each other again eventually.
And there are plenty of other
cities we haven't checked yet.
So let's keep moving,
just like we have been.