Hey! Feast your eyes!
That's the capital of
the Holy Country of Millis.
Welcome to Millishion!
[GEESE]
And with that,
I'm afraid this is
where I leave you.
[RUDEUS]
Huh? All the way out here?
At least stay until
we get inside--
We'll see each
other again, boss!
You don't have to miss me.
Then go.
But you better teach me how
to cook next time, you got it?
Gods, you're persistent.
Why do you want to learn
so badly, anyway?
'Cause, you know.
[RUDEUS]
No, Eris, I don't.
Why don't you
spell it out for me?
Come on, say it!
[GEESE]
Anyway, stay safe, big guy!
You as well. Don't get into
too much trouble.
[GEESE]
No promises!
Oh! Almost forgot!
Make sure you swing by
the Adventurers' Guild, okay?
Uh, yeah, can do.
[GEESE]
See ya!
[RUDEUS]
Listen up!
I hereby call this Dead End
team meeting to order.
Clap, everybody.
[ERIS giggles]
[RUDEUS] Well, gang, it's been
a year and a half since
Eris and I were teleported
to the Demon Continent.
And we've finally, finally made
it back to human territory!
Won't be long before we're home!
But if it's all right
with you two,
I think we should stay put
for a month or so
and pick up a few
jobs in the area.
Seriously?
[RUDEUS] I've heard
Guild jobs around here
are supposed to pay really well.
Saving up could solve some
problems before they arise.
Especially considering
we don't know yet
what the next boat
is gonna cost us.
Aww! But I don't wanna
take another stupid boat.
Since "Dead End" isn't
a well-known name here.
I've got a new gimmick for
"Operation Help Improve
the Superd's Reputation."
[RUDEUS] After we help someone,
we'll reveal Ruijerd's identity,
and give them one of
these figurines as a gift!
We can play it off like,
"These charms will calm
even the most savage Superd!
In a few short minutes,
they'll be like
a long lost brother
from another mother."
You know, somethin' like that.
I didn't realize you'd
made so many of these.
[RUDEUS] That said, I'd like
to take tomorrow off!
Why, are you sick?
[RUDEUS]
Oh, no.
I want to make a few
more of these figures,
and I wanna write a letter
before we get caught up in work.
A letter?
Yeah. I wanna write home
to let everyone know we're safe.
[RUDEUS] I should have written
a long time ago, honestly.
I just keep forgetting,
and it's not like I've
had a ton of free time.
My family must be worried sick.
I hope they're not mad.
Anything you wanna do?
As long as we have time,
then I wanna go goblin slaying!
I hear they show up
on the outskirts of town.
That sounds a little...
[ERIS screams]
[RUIJERD] She'll be fine.
Just let her give it a try.
Uh... You sure, though?
Well, okay, then.
Maybe you should go with her.
[ERIS] I think I can handle
a few stupid goblins!
[RUDEUS]
Talk about famous last words.
That settles that, I guess.
Go have fun tomorrow and I'll
see you both back here
in the evening.
Works for me!
[RUDEUS]
Follow her and keep her safe!
Come to think of it.
This is the first time
I've ever written to Paul.
I wonder what he'll
find harder to believe.
That I made friends
with a Superd?
Or that I got a magic eye from
the Great Emperor
of the Demon World?
[SMUGGLER 16A]
Move it!
That's not good.
Another kidnapping?
[RUDEUS] Must be
a pretty lucrative industry
in this world. I would
love to stay out of this
and not risk another
exciting stint in prison.
But I don't think
I have a choice.
I'm going.
[RUDEUS]
Rule one of Team Dead End.
Never abandon a child.
Rule two.
Never, ever abandon a child.
We can't, we're the good guys!
That's how we'll clear the
Superd name little by little.
[SMUGGLER 16A] You're sure
no one followed you?
[SMUGGLER 16B]
Yeah.
[SMUGGLER 16A]
Are you okay?
[SOMAL]
Uh-huh.
[SMUGGLER 16C] Hey, let the
boss know we got him.
[SMUGGLER 16D]
On it.
[RUDEUS]
How many of them are there?
And how do I get that
kid away from them?
I can't tell how strong
these guys are by looking,
so jumping out
and starting a fight
probably isn't
the smartest option.
I guess I'll play
the waiting game.
As long as they hold off
on the violence, anyway.
[RUDEUS] I wonder what this
hideout used to be. A church?
Looks like it's been abandoned
for a good long while.
Hmm, cloth.
It's a bit too small
to be clothing.
But something about it
is oddly soothing.
I recognize this texture.
This shape.
There should be...
Yep, three holes.
[RUDEUS]
Wait, these are panties!
Who goes there?
[RUDEUS]
Gah, not good.
[SMUGGLER 16B]
He's in the crate!
[SMUGGLER 16C]
Show yourself!
[RUDEUS] Damn these cowards
and their dastardly traps!
[SMUGGLER 16A] We've got an
intruder! Call for backup!
[RUDEUS sighs]
Here goes nothing.
[RUDEUS]
Hear me, you foul miscreants!
How dare you snatch
innocent children
from their families
and make them
prey to your twisted lust!
That's called kidnapping!
You should be ashamed!
What the hell do you
have on your face?
And who are you?
[RUDEUS]
Who am I?
I am the great
"Dead End" Ruijerd!
What was that?
Did you say Dead End?
[RUDEUS] Sorry, Ruijerd,
I just realized how this looks.
I will save the kid, though!
[SMUGGLER 16B] Go play hero
somewhere else, ya little punk,
we're in the middle of
something important.
[RUDEUS]
Sunrise Attack!
[SMUGGLERS scream]
[RUDEUS]
Are you hurt? Hey!
Weird. This kid seems familiar.
[VIERRA gasps]
Whoa! What happened?
You better watch yourselves.
He's young, but he's good.
That freak was in my laundry?
[RUDEUS] I am so sorry,
Ruijerd. I owe you one.
[RUDEUS chuckles]
You disgusting perv!
[SMUGGLER 16D]
That does it!
[yells]
[RUDEUS] C'mon, lady?
I can't look away!
Right. Left. Look at 'em go!
[SHIERRA]
Water Ball!
[gasps]
[VIERRA yells]
[RUDEUS]
Oop, so close!
Whew. That was a close one.
Stop scuttling around like
a cockroach! You deviant!
Just hold out and
wait for the captain.
[MAN]
Relax. I'm right here.
[RUDEUS]
Huh?
What? He's just some drunk.
[MAN] No reason to gang up on
some snot-nosed little brat.
[MAN]
I'll take him down personally.
[RUDEUS] Huh. He seems
really familiar to me, too.
But I can't place him
to save my life.
[RUDEUS gasps]
[MAN] This jackass
fights like he does.
[MAN yells]
[RUDEUS]
What is he, a dog?
[RUDEUS gasps]
[RUDEUS]
This guy.
[RUDEUS] He's way more
intense than his lackeys!
[gasps] No!
[MAN]
Rudy?
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
That's why he's familiar.
In this entire world,
there's only one man
who calls me by that name.
He's my one and only...
[RUDEUS]
Father?
So. Rudy.
Uh-- Long time, eh?
It's good to see you.
Yeah. I guess.
I... I'm just amazed
that you're still alive.
Oh. Thanks.
But uh, what are you doing
all the way out here?
Huh? "What am I doing here?"
You saw my message, right?
No. I... I guess not.
[RUDEUS] Yeah. What the heck
is he talking about?
I don't remember
getting any message.
Then, Rudy, what have you
been doing all this time?
It's kind of a long story,
but just surviving, mostly.
[RUDEUS]
If I have to break this down,
I might as well start with
the mana disaster in Roa.
So, part one.
I'll tell him how I met
my kindred spirit Ruijerd
and of the mayhem we made
in the city of Rikarisu.
Part two.
The great mage Rudeus
crosses the vast
Demon Continent,
righting various
wrongs with the help
of loyal sidekicks
Eris and Ruijerd.
Part three!
Our hero falls victim
to a devilish trap,
and finds himself
a helpless captive
in the Doldia village!
I can throw in a little
exaggeration for flavor,
but Paul doesn't
have to know that!
I think I'll leave out
the Man-God, though.
He is a pretty shady character.
Heh! In retrospect, the whole
trip was actually kinda fun.
[RUDEUS] And then when we
arrived in Wind Port,
the first thing
that met our eyes--
[PAUL]
All right.
[PAUL] I get the
picture already, kid.
You've spent the last year
and change playing around.
[gasps] No, we actually had
a lot of trouble out there.
[PAUL]
Oh, yeah? When?
You made it sound like
one big walk in the park.
Obviously. I told the story
that way on purpose.
And I realize I may have gotten
a little carried away, but...
So. Tell me, why didn't
you bother trying
to find out if anyone else
had been teleported
to the Demon Continent, hmm?
[RUDEUS]
Why didn't I?
There's really no good answer.
The only explanation
I can give is...
[RUDEUS]
I... didn't think about it.
I sorta had my hands full.
So you had plenty of time to
help some demon you'd never met,
but you couldn't bother
to spare a thought
for fellow victims
of a magical disaster?
[RUDEUS] Maybe I got
my priorities wrong. Fine.
No point in raking me over
the coals about it now.
The thought genuinely
never occurred to me!
What else do you want me to say?
You didn't look for anyone,
you didn't write,
but what did you do?
You went adventuring
with a cute little rich girl
like you were on
some kinda vacation.
You two even had an invincible
bodyguard with ya! Ha!
And then, the first thing you
decide to do in Millishion
is put some panties on your head
and pretend you're a hero?
Look, I didn't know where I was
or what I was doing.
But I knew I had to focus on
keeping Eris safe.
Can you really blame me
if I missed a few things
along the way?
[PAUL]
I'm not "blaming" you, kid.
Then why do you keep
taking jabs at me like this?
Remind me, that Eris girl
is Philip's daughter, right?
Yeah, of course.
I've never laid eyes on her,
but I bet she's a cutie.
Is that why you
never wrote to us?
Worried that all the extra
bodyguards you'd picked up
might get in the way of
your little love affair?
[RUDEUS]
I told you already!
I didn't write because
I just forgot!
Hey, Captain? Why don't
you just leave it at that?
He is still a child.
This is between me
and my son, thank you.
Please, sir.
You're the last person
who should be
lecturing me about
women, Father.
[PAUL]
Huh?
I didn't go blind over
the last year and a half.
And you two seem awfully close.
Do Mother and Lilia
know about her, or?
No, they do not.
How could they?
[RUDEUS] Oh, then you can be
as unfaithful as you like!
That's quite an outfit you've
got her wearing, by the way.
I guess I can expect
a new little brother
or sister any day no--
Enough with the bullshit, Rudy!
Look at me.
If you made it here,
that means you had to have
crossed through Zant Port?
So? What does that matter?
Don't play dumb with me!
[RUDEUS]
I'm not! I really don't know!
[PAUL]
Huh?
--Oh, yikes.
--Was that magic?
You little--
No! What do you want from me?
I did my best! Okay?
I was stranded in
a totally unfamiliar place!
I didn't have anyone to turn to!
And somehow I managed
to make it here alive!
Why isn't that good
enough for you?!
[PAUL] You could have
done better and you know it!
That's not true!
[RUDEUS]
What is wrong with you?
You never used to
look at me like that.
It's not fair, damn it!
[NORN]
Stop it!
Leave him alone!
Hey, Norn. Do you
remember me? I'm your--
Stop bullying my daddy, now!
Huh?
[RUDEUS]
I'm bullying him?
But... I...
Seriously? That's great.
[RUDEUS]
Forget it. I'm out.
There's obviously
nothing worthwhile
to see or do
in this stupid city.
I'll go back to the inn
and wait for Eris and Ruijerd.
Then we can get out of here.
Maybe tomorrow or the day after.
[PAUL] You're not the only one
who got teleported.
Everyone in Buena Village
was caught in the Calamity.
What did you say?
[PAUL] I left messages for you
at the Adventurer's Guild
in Zant and West Port.
You are an adventurer
now, aren't you?
Why didn't you read them?
While you were off enjoying
your vacation, people died!
[RUDEUS] Right. That mana
explosion was huge.
Why hadn't I thought of that?
Why did I think
Buena Village was fine?
So, if everyone is missing.
Does that mean Sylphie, too?
[PAUL] Figures. You're more
worried about your girlfriend
than your own mother, huh?
[gasps] Y-You mean you haven't
found Mother, either?
[PAUL]
No. There's no trace of her!
Or Lilia, or Aisha!
We've been looking, though.
For everyone who vanished.
That's the whole point of
the Search and Rescue Squad.
Why would a search and
rescue squad kidnap people?
[PAUL] Some of them
had been sold into slavery.
[gasps] Th-They what?
[PAUL] People were
teleported without warning
to all corners of the world,
and a lot of them were
taken advantage of.
Deceived and enslaved.
So we resorted to
forced liberation.
[RUDEUS]
Of course!
That was one of the kids
who used to bully Sylphie!
I was so sure
you had pieced it together
and started doing something
to help a long time ago.
But not you.
You were out sightseeing!
[RUDEUS gasps]
Okay. We can figure this out.
We both got a little
emotional today,
but it's not our first fight.
Once I get him to calm down,
we can plan our
next moves together
and it'll be like
nothing ever happened.
So first thing tomorrow
I'll go back to that bar,
and see if he...
[RUDEUS retching]
I'm back, Rudeus!
Get a load of this!
After I was done
slaying goblins, I got...
[ERIS gasps] Who was it?
Who did this to you?
[RUDEUS]
I'm fine.
You're obviously not!
So what happened?
I ran into my father
this afternoon.
[ERIS gasps]
Did he say something
to upset you?
Why would he?
You haven't seen
each other in so long!
[RUDEUS]
Well...
I'll murder him! Let go of me!
Don't interfere with
family squabbles.
He doesn't deserve
to be so miserable
after working so hard for us!
His father should be ashamed!
If he's miserable, perhaps
you ought to comfort him.
[gasps]
Everything's fine. Okay?
I'm here for you.
I'm sorry, Rudeus.
I'm... not very good
at this sort of thing.
It's okay.
You're doing great. Thank you.