Wow! Look, Rudeus!
It's the ocean!
[ERIS giggles]
It's salty!
Yeah, now that I think about it.
You've never seen
the ocean before, have you?
Let's jump in!
But we don't have bathing suits.
I bet we could find some--
[ERIS] I don't know
what that is. Hold this!
[RUDEUS]
Hold up.
Does that mean
she's going to swim naked?
Well. Eris is 13 now.
And it's been a while
since I snuck a peek.
[RUDEUS chuckles]
[RUIJERD]
I would advise against it.
This sea is teeming
with monsters.
[RUDEUS, ERIS]
Come on!
[TALHAND] Oh! We made it!
Solid ground at last!
Ugh, don't be such a baby.
You see what I
have to deal with?
[TALHAND]
Hey! Who you callin' a baby?
Huh? Get back here!
[ROXY sighs]
You two can fight later.
Please don't forget
why we're here!
And don't wander too far off!
[CAPTAIN 12A]
Wait a sec.
You guys're
"Dead End," aren'tcha?
Huh?
Word about you three has been
makin' the rounds lately.
"Mad Dog" Eris, right?
And "Guard Dog" Ruijerd.
[RUDEUS]
Whoa! We've got nicknames?
And you're...
Gimme a sec. It's, uh...
[RUDEUS]
The suspense is killing me!
I just hope it's not
"horndog" or something.
Oh, yeah! Rudjerd!
"Kennel Master" Rudjerd!
Huh?
[CAPTAIN 12A]
All righty...
[RUDEUS]
Really?
Sure, I borrow his name
sometimes to help boost his rep,
but can I be my own dude
for five seconds?
I've busted my buns
for a year now!
Gimme a little recognition!
"Kennel Master" isn't
a bad nickname, though.
I'd love to muzzle
Eris sometimes.
[gasps] Two hundred
green ore coins?!
Let's call this
meeting to order.
We need to discuss our funds.
Ruijerd's passage by ship
will cost 200 green ore coins.
That's more than
we've made in a year.
Even if we prioritize
S-ranked jobs,
we may never raise enough.
Yeah, that's no good.
We're not gonna--?
We can't leave him here!
Of course not.
That's out of the question.
Okay, then what are we gonna do?
I'm not sure yet.
I need a little
more time to think.
I have an idea.
What if you run
across the ocean?
[RUIJERD]
That is not a skill I possess.
[ERIS]
Aww. That woulda been cool.
[RUIJERD]
Rudeus. Please forgive me.
This is all my fault.
I'll keep trying to think
of something else, too!
It'll all work out.
Let's take a couple of days
to scout our options!
Thank you both.
[RUDEUS] How am I going to
get us out of this one?
Hey there! It's been a while.
[RUDEUS groans] Here I thought
I'd seen the last of
Mr. stupid no-face.
Oh! Well, my advice landed you
in real hot water
the last time around.
So I wanted to
give you some space.
I was embarrassed.
How 'bout that, even gods
have a sense of shame.
I meant for you to turn those
pet thieves into the guards.
You could've bonded
with Ruijerd over it all.
But no, you decided
to recruit them!
I never saw that coming!
Though, I gotta admit,
I had a blast
watching it play out.
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, well, it sucked for me.
Hey. If you hadn't've
gone through all that,
you may not've made it this far!
[RUDEUS]
So the ends justify the means?
Naturally,
results are everything!
You're a real jag.
It's not an apology,
but I've got more advice.
Buy some food
from a street vendor
and take a stroll through
the back alleyways.
Show me on the doll
where I asked.
Though might as well ask why.
[chuckles]
I can't tell you
everything, friend!
Wouldn't wanna
spoil the surprise.
So, then. I'll be on my way.
Hey!
[MAN-GOD]
Mmbye!
[RUDEUS] You can't just
come and go as you please!
[RUDEUS sighs]
So, uh. Rudeus said
we should split up today.
What do you think he's up to?
Your focus should stay
on your opponent!
[gasps]
You're wide open!
I did it.
I did it! I landed a hit!
[ERIS]
Yes! I did it! I won!
I'm getting stronger!
I'm amazing!
[RUDEUS]
This seems pointless.
I'm not sure what that
self-proclaimed "god"
wants from me.
Other than the joy of watching
me overcomplicate everything.
So this time,
I'm gonna follow their
instructions to the letter.
I won't think about it
too hard or stray off course.
That'll keep 'em from
having any fun! [chuckles]
[RUDEUS] Wait. Doesn't that
just make me a puppet?
[RUDEUS gasps]
[RUDEUS] I wonder what
Roxy's doing right now.
[ELINALISE]
Ahh! Yes! Get me, beast man!
I'll grab you by
the elf ears, yes!
I'm almost--!
[RUDEUS] Ohh... Oop, nope I'll
take care of you later, lil guy.
[RUDEUS]
Really? Her?
[KISHIRIKA]
Delicious! Yes! Amazing!
That's scrumptious!
[KISHIRIKA]
You have my deepest thanks.
This will sustain me for
another year, at least.
[RUDEUS] I doubt it.
What are you, an isopod?
[KISHIRIKA]
Now! Your name, peasant!
Hello, my name is
Rudeus Greyrat.
[KISHIRIKA]
I see!
And I am Kishirika Kishirisu!
Also known as...
...the Great Emperor
of the Demon World!
Yeah!
[KISHIRIKA]
[RUDEUS]
This poor kid.
Playing "Demon Emperor"
out here alone.
All right. I'll play along.
[RUDEUS] Of course!
I beg your pardon, my liege!
[gasps] Aw, yeah!
Now that's what's up!
That's the kind of reaction
I've been waiting for!
Most of the youth these days
don't know their manners, so!
I was simply ignorant of
Your Majesty's resurrection!
I do hope you can forgive
my impertinence.
Yes, very well, but only once!
Hm?
Oh. Uck. That's nasty!
What's your deal?
You're so freaky-lookin'!
What are you?
What aren't you?
Did you eat your twin
in the womb or something?
[RUDEUS] A toddler
dressed like a succubus
thinks I'm the freak? Sure.
Now, it's clear that your
generosity saved my life.
So! I shall grant you one wish!
Okay. I'd like fabulous wealth?
Out of the question!
Isn't it obvious
that I'm flat broke?
Right. Well then how
about half the world?
You wanna rule
half of the whole world?
That's a big wish!
Unfortunately, I never
conquered the world,
so I don't have half to give.
Ah, that's too bad.
Guess you'll just have to
pay me with your body.
Oh, hey! That I can do!
You're quite young
to be so lecherous!
Kinda makes me worry
about your future...
I'm obviously kid--
[KISHIRIKA]
Please be gentle with me.
[RUDEUS gasping]
[KISHIRIKA]
Wait, I forgot!
I'm already engaged
in this incarnation!
[RUDEUS sighs]
Great, so money, the world,
and your body are all out.
What can you give me?
Foolish mortal!
When the Great Emperor
Kishirika offers you a gift,
you choose a demon eye!
Sounds great.
How much are they worth?
They're not worth any money!
So don't even think
about selling it!
[RUDEUS]
Hmm, I see.
All right, what kind
do you wanna give me?
I think I know just the thing.
'Kay.
[RUDEUS screams]
Pipe down, you big weenie,
boys aren't supposed to cry.
[RUDEUS]
Damn you!
My eye! My eye!
See, you're fine.
Pretty cool, amiright?
Thanks once again
for all the food!
If you're ever in a bind,
don't hesitate to call on me!
Fare thee well!
Away!
[gasps]
[cackles]
[RUDEUS] And that's how I
gained the Eye of Foresight.
I don't understand
how I'm supposed to
adjust to this stupid thing.
Ah? You wanna learn
to watch where
you're walkin', there, asshole?
[RUDEUS] I'm so sorry.
My eyes aren't very good.
Heh. Yeah, well,
be more careful.
Not everyone's
as friendly as me.
Hey! You hear me?
I'm talkin' to you!
[gasps]
You little--
Huh?
[RUIJERD]
You met the Great Emperor?
I had no idea
that she'd returned.
[RUDEUS]
Do you know her?
[RUIJERD] I've never met her,
no, but I've heard plenty.
Her name is Kishirika Kishirisu.
As you now know, she can bestow
demon eyes on her followers.
She herself possesses
12 of varying effects.
[RUDEUS]
So what is she doing here?
[RUIJERD]
Who can say?
I don't know what runs through
the minds of emperors and kings.
Kneel before me maggots!
I guess none of us do.
[RUDEUS] I'm sorry,
but I think I should stay
in the room until
I get used to this eye.
That's fine with me!
Thank you for
understanding. Uh...
Eris. There's no guarantee
Kishirika is still in town.
Yeah, I know that!
But I'm gonna go
look for her anyway!
[RUIJERD]
Good luck.
[ERIS]
All right, Ruijerd, let's go!
Come on, hurry up!
[RUDEUS] It took me
about a week to really
get the hang of this
foresight business.
[RUDEUS] It was surprisingly
easy once I got a feel for it.
A lot like silent
spellcasting, actually.
I control my mana
to adjust my vision.
The more mana I channel,
the further into
the future I can see.
Like a temporal telescope.
I hope you're ready
for a beatdown!
That eye's not gonna save you!
[RUDEUS] If I really focus,
I can see about
two seconds ahead,
sometimes more.
Here we go!
But. She's blurry!
And I can see three of her?
They're different possibilities!
If I want to see clearly,
I can't look that far.
Now she'll slash from the right!
Yes!
[RUDEUS]
Here it comes!
She'll act like I beat her,
and then throw sand in my eyes!
Then a headbutt! Leapfrog!
[RUDEUS] And before she
tries to counterattack,
I'll pin her down for the win!
That's enough.
[gasps] Yes!
[ERIS]
Rudeus. You did really good.
Thank you.
Ha!
[ERIS]
I'm leaving!
Eris--
You fought
incredibly well, Rudeus.
I once knew a Superd
warrior with a demon eye,
but he died before
he was able to master it.
Learning to control one
in a week is exceptional.
[RUDEUS]
You mean that?
Do you think I could
even win against you now?
You can try it.
'Kay!
I shoulda known I didn't stand
a chance against Ruijerd.
I heard you got a pretty good
hit in on him, though!
You've gotten really strong!
[ERIS] Stop. You don't
have to comfort me.
[ERIS]
It's not fair.
You're good at everything and
I'm stuck trying to catch up.
[RUDEUS]
I'm sorry.
[ERIS]
I don't need you to apologize.
[RUDEUS]
She's absolutely right.
It's not like I worked hard
for this eye or anything.
Why'd I get so excited
about beating Eris
with a power I
stumbled on by accident?
It's basically cheating.
[RUDEUS] Not to mention
I've wasted a whole week
leveling up when
I'm supposed to be
focused on finding ways
to get us home.
Where do you think
you're going at this hour?
[RUDEUS gasps] Just thought
I'd check out the brothel.
And I take it you require
your staff to bed a woman?
[RUDEUS] Uh, yeah,
I thought I'd try some,
you know. Mage kink.
You're selling it, aren't you?
[RUDEUS]
N-No.
Yes.
I can't allow that.
I know how important
that staff is to you
as a mage and a man.
Just like this is.
[RUDEUS]
Yeah. Eris had it specially made
for my birthday last year.
This staff and that necklace
are the most
important things I own.
So in a similar situation,
would you sell off this pendant?
If I had to, yes.
Are you serious?
Have I still not earned your
trust after all this time?
What? I trust you!
[RUIJERD]
Then talk to me.
I'm perfectly capable
of rational discussion.
I'd like to think I've
learned some things
about the world since I met you.
I've learned how feared
and deeply despised
my people are to this day.
And now, we're faced with
an impossible sum
as a direct result.
And in spite of all that,
you still want to
cross the ocean with me.
Do you understand?
I caused this problem,
and I would like to be
part of the solution.
So just tell me.
Why do you insist on shouldering
this burden all alone?
We've gone a week
without any leads,
and we can't stay here forever.
So the way I see it,
we only have two options:
I can sell my staff
or we can look for
a ship to stow away on.
But the problem there is...
Working with a smuggler,
a criminal,
would compromise your values.
Even if it works,
I'm not willing to
fracture our party over it.
[RUDEUS]
So let's just play by the rules.
I'll sell my staff
for the money we need
to pay our fare legitimately.
It's the smartest way
to go about this.
Listen, Rudeus.
I appreciate your consideration.
But know this: I would never
surrender my weapon,
and you shouldn't, either.
My pride won't allow it.
[RUIJERD]
Besides.
[gasps]
[RUIJERD]
What would Eris think?
Giving up your staff would
"fracture our party"
just as badly.
For you, I'll turn
a blind eye to all evil
until we've made it
across the ocean.
[gasps]
I've made my choice.
Go look for your
smugglers, Rudeus.
And we'll get through
this together.
That's the end
of the discussion.
Speaking to each other
from the heart is hard work.
But it's always worth it, yes?
[RUIJERD]
Who's there?
Ooh, couple of tough guys!
Relax. I'm not here to
pick a fight or nothin'.
Just wanted to say thanks
for saving my noggin
from gettin' busted open.
Oh, you're the guy
from the other day.
Yep. It's a pleasure to
meet you all proper-like.
The name's Gallus Cleaner.