[RUDEUS] Bad things
always happen suddenly.
You suddenly lose your parents.
Your siblings suddenly beat
the living crap out of you.
[RUDEUS]
A truck suddenly runs you over.
[RUDEUS] You're suddenly
reborn in another world.
Your father suddenly
attacks you and
ships you off to tutor
a young noblewoman.
You're suddenly teleported
to another continent.
Or maybe that's just me.
[RUDEUS] But one thing is true
no matter who you are:
sometimes, people suddenly die.
[ERIS]
Hey! Rudeus!
Hurry up!
Yeah, yeah.
[RUDEUS pants]
[ERIS coughing]
You gotta tell me
what happened next!
[roaring]
Oh, Look! It's a bunch
of red dragons!
I wanna hunt
one of those someday!
[RUDEUS chuckles]
[RUDEUS giggles]
[panting]
[RUDEUS]
Heads up!
Thanks a bunch.
And here's one for you!
[RUIJERD]
Thank you.
Listen up.
I'm listening.
From this day forward,
you may call yourself a warrior.
Are you saying I...?
You're an adult now, Eris.
[ERIS gasps]
But! No.
I've still never defeated
you in a fair fight!
That doesn't matter.
You already possess
strength on par with
some of the greatest
warriors of our age.
He's right. Congratulations!
Wait. Hey, Rudeus?
This isn't a dream, is it?
Ooh! You should pinch me.
You're not gonna
punch me, are you?
No, dummy, just do it!
[ERIS] I didn't say
you could pinch me there!
[RUDEUS] Sorry. But at least
we know you're not dreaming,
'cause I wouldn't be in
this much pain if you were!
[gasps] I'm a warrior.
But don't let it
go to your head.
That also means
I won't treat you
as a child any longer.
Understand?
[ERIS]
Yes!
Rudeus! Look!
[ERIS] We don't need to
take this stupid detour,
we have Ruijerd with us!
So, let's cut straight
through the mountains
and go fight some dragons!
Be reasonable, Eris.
Come on, you could
take one, couldn't you?
Are you kidding? There's no way!
Red dragons are supposed to
be incredibly strong
and they live in flocks!
They swarm!
We can't just waltz
through their territory!
Back me up, here, Ruijerd.
[RUIJERD]
He's right.
[ERIS]
Aw, really?
[RUIJERD] Yes. Even among
the Seven Great Powers,
there are those who would
likely turn back halfway.
[RUDEUS] Wait, are you talking
about the Gods we saw
listed on that stela along
Holy Sword Highway?
I would have thought
people as strong as them
could easily dispatch
a dragon. Wow.
[RUIJERD]
They could slay one.
But only the mightiest
champions could ever
hope to stand against
an entire flock of them.
That's incredible.
So that would be
the Technique God,
who's at number one, and the
Dragon God at number two. Right?
I wonder what that kind of
power even looks like.
Hey, what's gotten into you two?
[gasps]
[NANAHOSHI gasps]
Stay right where you are.
Don't move a muscle.
Either of you.
[roars]
[gasps]
[ORSTED] Is that Ruijerd
Superdia I hear?
[ORSTED] And you must be
Eris Boreas Greyrat.
But you, I don't recognize.
Who the hell are you two?
And how do you know who I am?
Yeah, explain yourself
this instant!
This is a curious place to meet
you, but it's not important.
[NANAHOSHI]
It's not?
There's nothing I can
do about it now. Excuse us.
[RUDEUS]
Please, wait!
[BOTH gasp]
[ORSTED]
Who are you?
Oh, beg your pardon.
My name is Rudeus Greyrat.
[ORSTED]
A Greyrat, you said?
[RUDEUS]
Uh, yes. Um.
Would you mind
telling us who you are?
My name is Orsted.
Nice to meet you, Orsted.
So, uh, how did you come to be
acquainted with my friends?
[ORSTED]
I'm not. Not yet.
[RUDEUS]
"Yet"? What does that mean?
[ORSTED]
You don't need to know that.
Tell me this.
Which branch of the Greyrats
are you from?
Who are your parents?
Zenith and Paul Notos Greyrat.
[ORSTED] Hm. Paul shouldn't have
a son, only two daughters.
[RUDEUS]
Well, that was rude.
Paul does indeed have a son,
and he takes after his father.
But, uh, how does this guy
know about my sisters?
[RUIJERD]
Stop! Don't come any closer!
[ORSTED]
Boy. I notice you match my gaze.
I'd love to stop
as soon as possible,
that look in your eyes
is terrifying.
Interesting.
Now, what exactly did you want?
Oh, I just... For some reason,
it seemed like you
might know something
about the mana disaster.
I don't.
[RUDEUS] All right, then.
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
[ORSTED]
I wonder.
Are you perhaps familiar
with the name "Man-God"?
[RUDEUS] Oh, I am!
He's appeared in my dreams and--
So that's it.
[RUIJERD]
Rudeus!
[ORSTED] I should have known you
were an apostle of the Man-God.
Take Eris and run!
[yells]
[RUDEUS gasps]
[gasps]
[ERIS yells]
You have great potential,
Eris Boreas Greyrat.
You've improved considerably,
but you lack polish.
[RUDEUS coughing]
[ORSTED] When you die,
give the Man-God a message.
Tell them Dragon God Orsted
is about to end this
once and for all.
Let the great protection of fire
converge where thouseekest.
I call the bold heat
of a torch, here.
And now: Fireball!
Cast without incantation?
So, did the Man-God
give you that power?
[RUDEUS coughing]
That's quite enough of that.
Disturb Magic.
Heh. Well aren't you
a crafty one?
[coughs]
Open Front Wyrmgate.
What an incredible
quantity of mana.
He may rival Laplace.
[coughs]
[ORSTED] Why don't you use
silent magic to heal your lungs?
[ORSTED]
No matter. Die.
[gasps] H-Hey, Rudeus? Rudeus!
[RUDEUS]
This doesn't look good.
I don't want to die.
I haven't gotten to make good
on my promise with Eris yet.
I'm coming, okay?
[RUDEUS]
It's just two years.
I can hold on for
two more years.
Then, I'll be able to
die without regrets.
[ERIS]
Rudeus!
[RUDEUS]
Yeah. It's one wound.
I can do this.
Let me just gather my mana.
I can't die yet...
Focus and I'll be fine...
[screams]
We're leaving, Nanahoshi.
[NANAHOSHI]
Ah. Sure.
[ERIS] Ruijerd!
Ghislaine! Grandfather!
Father! Mother!
Anyone!
Someone, help! I don't care who!
[RUDEUS]
Eris, I'm sorry...
[ERIS]
Someone save him!
[NANAHOSHI] Orsted.
I just thought of something.
What if he...?
Hey!
[MAN-GOD] Welp, that, uh...
That was a shame.
"A shame"? I suppose that's
one way to put it.
[MAN-GOD chuckles]
You know, you're acting
kinda different today.
Are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
Well, I do have this wide,
gaping hole in my chest.
Hey, can I ask you
something, God-y?
[MAN-GOD]
Shoot.
[RUDEUS]
That Orsted guy attacked me
the second he found out
I knew you.
So, uh... Why is that?
[MAN-GOD]
He's the wicked Dragon God!
Despite how good
and virtuous I am,
he holds great
enmity towards me.
"Virtuous," huh?
Well, I bet you still find
plenty of ways to make enemies.
But wait. If that's the case,
why not let me know that I was
about to run into him?
A heads up
would've been helpful.
Yeah, sorry.
Sadly, I can't see
anything to do with him.
Not his present, or his future.
So, I honestly had no idea
you'd run into him, either!
That's kinda weird.
Do you know why?
[MAN-GOD] He's got a curse that
makes me unable to see him.
[RUDEUS] Really?
So, curses are real, too?
[MAN-GOD]
Yup. There are these weirdos
called "Cursed Children."
Like Blessed Children,
but, uh, more unfortunate.
Orsted is one of them.
He's got about
four curses total.
[RUDEUS]
Hmm.
[MAN-GOD] Ooh! You saw
how scared Ruijerd
and Eris were of him, right?
That's the really big one.
Every living creature
in this world
either hates him or fears him.
Well, that sounds
pretty damn unpleasant.
I've been hated,
but on that scale?
[RUDEUS]
That's gotta suck.
[RUDEUS] Except. I didn't hate
or fear him, so what gives?
[MAN-GOD] I would assume
that's because you
came from a whole
different world.
[RUDEUS] How would being from
another world make me immune?
I don't know, but it was the
same with Ruijerd, wasn't it?
Yeah. Hang on.
What does that mean?
Are you saying Ruijerd
is a Cursed Child, too?
[MAN-GOD] No, no, that's
the curse of the spears.
During the war,
Laplace transferred his
curse of fear to his
own fancy weapons,
and passed those on
to the Superd tribe.
That's right. Well,
that's convenient for him.
So Ruijerd is--
Wait, have you known this
from the beginning?
Did you tell me to help him
already knowing
it wasn't going to do any good?
Oh, no, don't get
the wrong idea!
The curse on the Superd will
gradually fade away with time.
Now, a bit of it does still
remain with Ruijerd himself,
but since he started
shaving his head,
the effects have
been greatly reduced.
Why is that?
Because Laplace
also had green hair!
Ha... You say that like it's
supposed to make sense.
Is that really how
curses work here?
[MAN-GOD] Yep! Anyway,
the curse on him is fading
because of his
involvement with you!
The deep-rooted prejudice
against him isn't,
but with enough hard work
he can overcome that, too!
So, it wasn't a total
waste after all.
That's good to hear, at least.
[RUDEUS] I'm still shocked that
he was taken out so easily.
Never thought I'd see the day.
[MAN-GOD] Oh yeah,
Ruijerd's no match for Orsted.
[RUDEUS] Well, he is one of
the Seven Great Powers.
How could we have beaten him?
You couldn't.
The Dragon God is unmatched,
even after you factor in all
those curses holding him back.
Really? I thought
I remembered that
the Dragon God was
only ranked number two.
Is he not?
[MAN-GOD] The Technique God
is ranked number one,
but Orsted would destroy him
if they went toe to toe.
Actually, at his full power,
he could probably destroy
this whole world.
But, too bad, so sad.
His curses won't let him!
Weird, though.
You sure know a lot about a guy
you "can't see any
past or future for."
[chuckles] Well, you know.
Hey, it's whatever.
At this point,
I couldn't care less
what you're hiding from me.
I appreciate how much
you care about Ruijerd.
Not to mention, I never would've
rescued Lilia and
Aisha without you.
So compared to all that,
what are a few little godly
white lies sprinkled
in for flavor?
It's not like I'll ever
see you again, anyway.
You won't?
[RUDEUS]
Nah, or I mean, I assume not.
I'm dead as hell, right?
[MAN-GOD]
I get it!
So that's why you've
given up on everything.
Aw, just the opposite
of our first meeting.
Yeah, 'cause, that time,
I only thought I was dead
and I didn't have any idea
what the heck was going on.
[RUDEUS] This time, well,
that's life, huh?
I just got unlucky.
Although, I guess
I shouldn't say that.
Unfinished business aside,
how many people get
a second shot at life at all?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah. I am lucky.
Welp, I guess this is
where we say goodbye.
You got any idea how I'm
supposed to pass on from here?
[MAN-GOD chuckles]
No, sorry.
But I do have some
good news for you!
[RUDEUS]
Huh?
Kid. You're not dead yet.
[RUDEUS]
Wha--?
Rudeus! You're awake now?
[RUDEUS retching]
[ERIS]
Rudeus!
[RUDEUS coughing]
[panting]
Are you okay?
[RUDEUS]
Why am I alive?
[ERIS]
Uh, just a minute ago,
that girl said something
I couldn't hear
and the Orsted guy came back
and cast a healing spell.
What girl?
I think he called her Nanahoshi?
[RUDEUS] Nanahoshi?
The masked one, right.
Why would he want to heal
somebody he just killed?
[ERIS] He'll be fine.
They said he's just knocked out.
That's good to hear.
Why are you so
enthusiastic right now?
[RUDEUS]
I dunno.
I just feel like everything
in me is overflowing.
So, you won't mind if
I punch you, then?
[RUDEUS]
Not a bit.
I'm sorry I
made you worry, Eris.
You better be, you dummy.
[ERIS]
I'm so glad.
You're alive. I'm so glad.