[GHISLAINE]
You can keep sleeping.
[ERIS] No, I'm fine.
Besides, it's dawn.
[VILLAGER 23A]
Hey!
You grow nice and strong, now.
[VILLAGER 23A]
Things will be back to normal
sooner than we think,
I believe it.
Yeah.
[STUDENT 23D giggles]
[STUDENT 23A]
C'mon, c'mon! Move it.
[STUDENT 23B] That's your cue
to scatter, cockroaches.
[STUDENT 23A]
What're you thinkin'?
--[STUDENT 23B] Prob'ly udon.
--[STUDENT 23C] Again?
Hey. Didn't you learn
not to cut in line
back in elementary school?
[STUDENT 23A]
Still wanna run your mouth?
Hope the tough-guy act
was worth it, fatass!
[STUDENTS laugh]
[STUDENT 23A]
Drop dead!
[STUDENT 23B]
That one sounded nasty!
[STUDENT 23C]
At least try to dodge 'em!
[STUDENTS laugh]
Hey, you know what could be fun?
[knocking]
[FATHER]
Can we come in?
Hell no!
[BOTH gasp]
[MOTHER]
Are you all right, love?
How are your bruises?
[FATHER]
I know how hard this must be,
but you can't give in
to punks like that!
We'll get those kids expelled.
[MOTHER]
Just leave it to us.
You take it easy
and rest for now.
[FATHER]
Well. Be strong, hang tight.
Your mother and I are going to
talk to the school
again right now.
[MOTHER] I'm leaving some food
right outside your door.
Please eat it, okay?
[RUDEUS]
"Strong." Yeah, right.
If I was, then I'd...
[RUDEUS sobbing]
Young Master Rudeus.
I'd say it's high time
you got out of bed.
And since you don't appear
to be otherwise occupied,
I'd like to enlist your
help in a few matters.
Namely, improving
our infrastructure.
Our agricultural
efforts have suffered
due to our distance
from the river.
But I imagine using
earth magic to dig
a few wells should be
no trouble for you.
What do you say?
We'll also soon feel
a greater need
for proper housing,
rather than tents.
Unfortunately,
we lack the manpower.
Not to mention...
With regard to dear Lady Eris.
I intend to report
that she tragically
perished following the
teleportation incident.
[ALPHONSE]
Of course, revealing that now
would likely hinder our
reconstruction efforts.
So the official announcement
won't be for some time yet.
I'm real sorry to hear she
ran out on you like that.
I intend to restore Fittoa
to its former glory,
with or without the young miss.
Then I suggest you leave
me alone and get to work.
Given what transpired
between you and Lady Eris,
I thought allowing you to
rest idly would be a kindness.
But as refugees continue
to pour in from Millishion,
we're running short
on both tents and food.
So that's it.
You're here to kick me out.
On the contrary,
I'm here to remind you
that you aren't
the only one suffering.
What should I have
done differently?
[RUDEUS] Just tell me
what you want from me.
You're positive this is
what you want?
We can't thank you
enough, dear sir!
I'll repay you some day!
Oh, Saint Millis...
Yeah, if you hadn't shown up
just in the nick of time,
we all would have been this
thing's shit before too long!
No kidding, you must be a crazy
high-ranked adventurer
to pull that off!
What's your name?
[RUIJERD] I'm Ruijerd
of the party Dead End.
[MERCHANT 23A]
I've never heard of you!
Where are you from?
Judging by the designs
on your clothes,
are you a demon?
[ERIS]
Rudeus is an amazing person.
He's smart,
and talented, and strong.
And he's only getting stronger.
He faces every challenge head-on
and learns something
from every failure.
He's amazingly amazing.
You know, as long as
he was with me,
I didn't have to be afraid.
Yes, I'm a Superd.
[ALL]
A real Superd?
Well, that's... Okay, then.
I've never seen one of you guys
in real life before.
I haven't either.
I've only heard of you
in bedtime stories.
Can I ask something?
Is it true that you have that
gem-looking thing in your head?
[ERIS] So it never occurred
to me that he could die.
But he did.
And once I realized
I wouldn't have been
able to save him on my own,
I started to worry that I was
just a burden on him.
[ALL gasp]
Wow, that looks nothing
like I pictured it!
I'm gonna brag to everyone
about this when we get back!
[RUIJERD]
I see.
So, then none of you
fear me, I take it?
[ADVENTURER 23B]
Are you kidding?
How could we when you just
saved our hides
from certain death?
No doubt I would have been
when I was a child, though.
He's done so much for me,
and all I've done
is hold him back.
I relied on him too much,
and that's just not fair to him.
[ERIS] I always forget that he's
younger than me. Smaller.
You too, huh?
My pop would tell me a Superd
would eat me, and I'd jump.
We don't eat children.
[MERCHANTS laugh]
[MERCHANT 23A]
No, of course you don't!
And here's the truth:
I love Rudeus!
[ERIS] But I'm not fit
to be with him yet.
So I'll get stronger until I
know I can walk alongside him.
And then we'll meet again
and take the next step together.
Jeez, it got cold fast,
didn't it?
[ZANOBA gasps]
I shall never tire of
marveling at its majesty!
Master Rudeus!
I, your humble pupil Zanoba,
will count the days until our
inevitable glorious reunion!
I'm roastin' out here!
Bet the boss could
conjure up some water
and cool us both down
without breaking a sweat.
I hate this!
[LEO barks]
[NIECE]
This tastes great!
[FIRST BROTHER]
I'm glad!
Now get your elbows
off the table.
[NIECE] Can I make a plate
to take upstairs?
[FIRST BROTHER]
No, leave him alone.
[MOTHER]
I was gonna take him this one,
but since you offered,
will you go for me?
[NIECE]
Yeah, sure! Gimme!
[FIRST BROTHER] Mom. At least
wait until after dinner.
[NIECE]
I wish he could come out.
I hope he starts
feeling better soon.
[FIRST BROTHER]
I do, too.
[gasps]
[TAVER cheering]
Woxho! Rayqa! Rayqa!
[BOTH]
Hit me!
[TAVERN cheers]
Foolish mortals!
Victory is mine!
I did it! I did it!
I did it! [cackles]
I am unstoppable!
[sighs]
That ought to settle your debt,
but now I'm broke.
That's just great.
Now, now, don't waste precious
time dwelling on details!
Let me instead commend you
for your selflessness!
I'll happily reward you
for your aid!
I kinda doubt that.
We've already established that
you're completely penniless.
Though, I would like you
to pay me back somehow.
Well, as luck would have it.
You just happen
to be speaking with
the Great Emperor of
the Demon World...
Kishirika Kishirisu!
I may be short of coin,
but I can bestow
a demon eye upon you!
[sighs] I remember now.
In that case,
I would prefer that
you use your eyes
to find someone for me,
Your Majesty.
What? You would use your one
wish for the sake of another?
Bravo, how admirable!
Who is it you seek?
Your long-lost lover
or something?
That's not it.
I'm looking for
the missing family
of somebody named
Rudeus Greyrat.
Just leave it to me, then!
What was that
name again? Greyrat?
Oh! Ding, ding, ding, got 'em!
[ROXY]
Huh?
It's Daddy!
[PAUL]
Aisha.
It's been a long time.
I've missed you, my lord.
[PAUL]
Lilia.
It's all right. I'm here now.
What about Mommy?
I don't see her.
Master Rudeus did say
that she was still missing,
but I'd hoped...
[PAUL]
Norn, your mom is waiting for
your big brother
to come get her.
So just you wait.
We'll be together
before too long, 'kay?
[KISHIRIKA]
Ah-ha! The father, the maid,
and the two little girls
have been happily
reunited in Millishion!
That's amazing!
[KISHIRIKA]
Now, the mother is, uh...
Uh...
[KISHIRIKA]
Nope. Can't get a good look.
So, you can't see her?
But I thought you could
find anyone, Your Greatness!
[KISHIRIKA] Sorry. But I do know
her approximate location!
Then where is she?
[KISHIRIKA]
I believe
she's on the Begaritt Continent,
in the Labyrinth City of Rapan!
At any rate,
she is alive, isn't she?
[KISHIRIKA]
Mm-hm!
And what about Rudy?
[KISHIRIKA]
Hm? Right, hang on a sec.
Ah! Rudeus is back on
the Central Continent!
And boy oh boy, he's looking
depressed! [cackles]
Perhaps some food he scavenged
disagreed with him!
Oh, is that so?
Pardon my earlier
impertinence, Your Majesty.
I appreciate your help.
[KISHIRIKA]
Think nothing of it!
Consider us even!
Now, fare thee well! [cackles]
[ELINALISE]
The Begaritt Continent, hmm?
But if Zenith really is alive,
you have to wonder why
she hasn't contacted anyone.
[ROXY]
Hard to say.
But she could be
in some kind of trouble.
[ELINALISE] What should we do
about her son, then?
I'm not sure.
It does worry me a little to
hear he's been depressed, but...
[ROXY] If I know Rudy,
he'll get back up
on his own before too long.
[RUDEUS] People don't
bounce back that easily,
no matter how many
chances they get to do it.
It's easier to fall into a hole
than it is to climb out of one.
I was surrounded by
people who loved me.
Who reached out to me.
And I rejected them.
I was trapped
by my own paranoia.
Convinced that, regardless
of what they told me,
they were all laughing
at me behind my back.
I used to dream,
if I had just one more chance,
I could get back to normal.
Do things right.
But, too little, too late.
No one reaches out anymore.
And why would they?
I won't actually change.
And no one would
notice if I tried.
So, might as well
keep dreaming. Right?
[RUDEUS]
Keep dreaming.
Gotcha!
[PAUL]
Hey, Rudy!
[ZENITH]
Oh, no.
[RUDEUS]
That was too easy, Father!
I get the biggest
dinner plate tonight!
[PAUL] I beg to differ!
That was only if you won!
[RUDEUS] I landed a hit,
so I win by decision!
[PAUL]
Ah! Not so fast!
All right, listen up!
Throwing mud in
my eyes is cheating!
Yeah, but you were
the one who taught me
to pursue victory by
"any means necessary"!
[PAUL]
Ha!
Master Rudeus.
[RUDEUS]
Oh, yay! Thank you, Lilia.
My lord.
[PAUL]
Yes, thank you.
My goodness,
you got so dirty out there!
[RUDEUS chuckles]
Yeah, sorry.
[yawns]
Ah. Guess I'm
a little bit sleepy.
You're not getting sick,
are you, Mother?
Why don't you go to bed early?
I'll clean up in here!
Will you, now? Well, okay!
I might just
take you up on that.
Please do!
[ZENITH] But promise
you'll come wake me up
when you're done here, okay?
Yeah, I can do that!
I would be happy to take
responsibility for waking you!
[RUDEUS]
Father!
[RUDEUS] I need you
to take responsibility
for cleaning the floors!
Huh? Yeah, sure. In a sec.
Hey, sleepy girl.
[RUDEUS] Father,
you should know this by now!
We need to be as efficient
when it comes to cleaning
as we are with training,
so I'm gonna need you to...
[ZENITH]
Thank you so much, Rudy.
Yeah, it's the least
I can do for you!
You're my mom!
[ZENITH]
Rudy?
Yeah?
[ZENITH]
I love you.
[RUDEUS]
That's right.
I have to go. I...
I have to find Zenith.
[ELLEMOI]
Rudeus Greyrat, you say?
[CLEANE] How does one
become a Saint-class
water mage at age five?
And without incantations,
no less?
Provided that's all true,
I would love to
recruit him, but...
[LUKE]
It does sound so exaggerated
it's almost laughable.
But you would like us to believe
this is not hyperbole,
based on personal experience?
[FITZ]
I would. Yes.
Then tell me, what exactly is
your relationship to this man?
[FITZ]
He is my savior, my mentor,
and my first friend.
And, truth be told...
[FITZ]
If I had to pick one thing,
he's the person I respect most.