[RUDEUS]
Ah, shit.
[MAN-GOD]
Language!
Good to see you
haven't changed a bit.
[RUDEUS] I was this close
to forgetting about you.
[MAN-GOD] It's been a whole year
since our last chat.
But why the cold shoulder?
It's all thanks to me you got
that demon eye, you know!
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, sure.
But if you'd been
a little more specific.
I wouldn't have
wound up in prison,
missed Paul's message, or had
that stupid fight with him.
[laughs] Your adventures
never cease to entertain.
But lemme ask you this.
You sure you wanna
blame me for everything?
[RUDEUS]
Dammit.
Every time you bring me here,
I go back to my old self.
I swear I've
turned over a new leaf.
I take responsibility now!
All right, fine,
I'm ready to listen
and I'm grateful
for your guidance!
I wouldn't be alive without you,
is that what you wanted to hear?
Now hurry up and spit out
your next piece of advice!
My goodness, you never just
come out and beg me for it!
[RUDEUS]
Nope. But this time.
I have a specific request:
Help me find my family.
Whatever do you mean?
I thought your family was
in a whole other world!
You know exactly what I mean.
Zenith, Lilia, and Aisha, okay?
And, if possible,
I want to know about
Sylphie, Ghislaine,
Philip, and Sauros as well.
I dunno. Lemme think about it.
Aw, I'm only joking!
Tough crowd today.
But, before I tell you,
promise me one thing.
We'll see.
If the next advice
I give you helps you
reunite with your
long-lost family,
I would like for you to
trust me from now on!
Whaddya say?
What, and obey your
every command
like a little
yes-man marionette?
Oh, no. I won't ask
you to go that far.
I just mean it's gonna
get exhausting
if you're this hostile every
time we talk, you know?
For you, maybe,
but it's gonna be
exhausting for me either way.
Do you know how depressing
it is to be back in this body?
Every time you drag me here,
I feel like my
growth's been erased.
But I guess if you can
help me out this time,
I'll stop being so rude.
And you'll trust me, right?
That'll depend on
what happens next.
Okay! Guess that'll have to do.
[clears throat] Now, let's put
that demon eye to use.
[MAN-GOD] In a few weeks time,
you'll enter Shirone Kingdom.
Where you will stumble
upon this scene.
The young lady being detained is
none other than your
sister, Aisha Greyrat.
Hang on. What'd you just say?
[MAN-GOD] Rescue her,
but under no circumstances
should you tell her
your real name.
Use an alias.
Ask about details
of her situation.
And then send a letter
to your acquaintance
at the royal palace of Shirone.
Wait. Who do I know at--?
If you can do that,
then you shall succeed in
rescuing both Aisha
and Lilia from
the tyrant at the
palace of Shirone!
Lilia, too, huh? But why?
If they're in Shirone, they
should have been found by now--
[RUDEUS retching]
[RUIJERD]
What's wrong? Are you okay?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
Just some lingering
seasickness from earlier.
[RUDEUS] Did that freak lead me
to this eye just to show me
the future whenever
the mood strikes?
[RUDEUS] I don't get it.
I feel like I'm being used.
I'm not getting on another boat
for the rest of my life.
[ERIS]
I didn't know what to expect,
but this "rice" stuff is
actually pretty tasty!
Give it a try, Rudeus,
what are you waiting for?
Well. Thank you for this meal.
[ERIS]
Shirone's capital is so amazing!
[RUDEUS]
The Man-God told me to
write to "an acquaintance"
at the castle.
Meaning Roxy, I guess?
Supposedly I can "save"
Lilia and Aisha that way,
but if they're here in the city,
Roxy should have
found them ages ago. Right?
Ooh, this is where your
master lives now, isn't it?
Hey. So what's with
the gloomy expression?
[RUDEUS]
Well. I heard from a source
that some members of my family
may have been taken captive
somewhere in this kingdom.
[ERIS]
Really?
[RUIJERD]
Oh. Your mother?
[RUDEUS]
No, Lilia and Aisha.
Our former maid
and my little sister.
[ERIS]
Your sister?
How'd she get carted all the way
here from Millishion so fast?
That was Norn, my other sister.
Uh-huh.
Anyway, if you're up for it,
I'd really appreciate
any help you can give me
with gathering more
information about them.
Well, yeah.
If it's about your family,
then we don't have a choice.
[RUDEUS]
Thank you.
[RUDEUS] Thank god they didn't
ask who my source was.
Let's hope it stays that way.
I don't like keeping secrets.
But until I figure out what that
skinny, pale twerp is thinking,
I should be careful
who I tell about them.
[RUDEUS] I'd like to send this
to the royal palace, please.
[RUDEUS] There's one job down.
Roxy's gonna be so surprised!
Hope she gets back to me soon.
What now?
[RUDEUS] If I trust
the Man-God's advice
in its entirety, all I need
to do to find Aisha is
find the alleyway
from that vision, right?
But this city's so big.
And come to think of it, why was
she being detained outside?
The Man-God made it
sound like she was
being held captive
in the palace itself.
[RUDEUS]
Who is that? Ruijerd?
No. He's great at tailing
people. I'd never notice him.
And it's definitely not Eris.
If she wanted to come,
she wouldn't bother
sneaking around about it.
So what the heck?
Does someone in Shirone
have a grudge against me?
How could they?
I literally just got here!
[RUDEUS]
Wait. This alley is...
[gasps]
[AISHA]
Huh? How'd he do that?
Hey! Stop it!
No, give that back!
[SOLDIER 19A] You need to
keep it down. I'm begging you.
[SOLDIER 19A]
Please?
[AISHA]
Give me back my letter!
[SOLDIER 19B]
Come on.
[SOLDIER 19A] Apologies.
We're only doing our jobs.
Uh. Sorry! This isn't
what it looks like!
Okay. But you do realize
that's kinda hard to believe.
[SOLDIER 19A]
I hear ya, but listen, son.
He and I are soldiers from
the Shirone palace garrison.
This little girl got lost
wandering around,
and all we want to do
is escort her home.
But you guys stole my letter!
It's mine and I want it back!
Yeah, why would you
need to do that
if you're just trying to
get her home safely?
It's complicated, but adults
have their reasons.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Please! You'll help
me out, won't you?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Incantation-less magic! Is he?
[whistle blows]
Hand over the girl
and don't do anything stupid.
We don't want
anyone to get hurt.
Hold on tight, okay?
I'm getting us out of here.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[AISHA screams]
[AISHA] Oh, by the way,
my name is Aisha Greyrat!
Thanks so much for
saving me back there!
You have my sincerest gratitude!
[RUDEUS]
Wow. She's so well-mannered.
How old is she now? Six?
So, um. Would you mind telling
me what your name is, mister?
[RUDEUS]
Oh! Uh.
There are some who know me
as the Moonlight Knight!
Oh, wow! That's such
an incredible name!
[AISHA] My apologies
if this sounds ungrateful
after such a daring rescue,
but may I make
a selfish request?
Go ahead.
My mother has been
imprisoned in the castle,
so would you please
help me send this letter
to my father to inform him?
[RUDEUS] I see.
That's what that letter was.
Between that, her manners,
and her vocabulary,
she's one clever girl.
[RUDEUS] I'm happy to help,
but surely your mother
taught you that you need
money to send off a letter.
Oh, no, she taught me that
if a cute little girl like me
looks up with pleading eyes and
begs sweetly to send
her father a letter,
then other people will happily
take care of the rest!
[RUDEUS]
Lilia, you scoundrel.
I've already tried to
make contact with him
many times before but the people
in the castle won't let me.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
But, uh, do you have anybody
else you could count on to help?
Nobody.
What about, uh, a nice
young lady with blue hair
who your mother might know?
Or maybe a cool older
brother somewhere?
I do have a brother,
but I can't count on him.
[RUDEUS]
Excuse me?
Did I not just rescue you
in the coolest way possible?
[RUDEUS]
M-May I ask why not?
Yes, of course you may!
It all started out
with a box in our home
that my mother treasured.
She said never touch or open it,
but when I asked why,
she'd just say it was important
to my big brother
and it had to stay safe.
But one day, when my mother
was out of the house,
I snuck a peek.
And guess what I found in there?
Something totally appropriate?
It was panties!
My brother was
completely devoted to
a pair of women's underwear
before he was even
five years old!
And a small pair, too!
By my calculations,
they must have
belonged to a girl of about 14.
[RUDEUS] "Calculations"?
You're supposed to be six!
This kid's gonna be way
too smart for her own good.
I dunno, it sounds
like that could be
one big misunderstanding.
It's not, I was able to gather
more information to verify.
My brother used to spy on
that nice lady in the bathtub,
and on my father and his wife
when they were in bed!
He was shameless.
Mother wants to cover
it up to protect him,
but I am positive.
My older brother's
definitely a pervert!
Okey-dokey, then, sounds like
you got it all figured out.
That's really unfortunate.
[RUDEUS] Welp,
didn't see that one coming.
But I guess that's why the
Man-God told me to use an alias.
It's all coming
together now. Dammit.
If it's okay,
I would love to know what your
actual name is, Mister Knight!
That's a secret!
But most people will know me as
the "Kennel Master"
of the party Dead End.
Oh, wow.
A name like that has to have
an incredible story behind it.
I would love to hear it!
Another time!
For now, how's about I go
and rescue your mother, huh?
How are you gonna do that?
Don't you worry.
I got a couple tricks
up my sleeve!
So leave everything to me.
I'll show you what this
Kennel Master's made of!
[RUDEUS]
Okay, so, whenever she's around,
please only refer to me
as the "Kennel Master."
That's dumb,
why would we do that?
Because she's kinda developed
a misguided impression
about her big brother.
So if we're spending
time together,
I wanna fix that by
showing her my good side.
[sighs] I think
every side of you
is your good side, but whatever.
Aw, Eris.
Ugh. What's with that
creepy grin on your face
whenever I compliment you?
Welp, if we're gonna
be heroes, let's go!
I haven't stormed
a castle in ages.
[RUDEUS]
Whoa! Hang on!
Why should we?
I'd just feel more
secure if we waited
to hear from
my master first. 'Kay?
[whines]
[RUDEUS]
Gah, what a bunch of hotheads.
[GINGER]
Pardon me!
[RUDEUS]
Comin'!
[GINGER]
Would you be Lord Rudeus?
[RUDEUS]
I would.
I am a member of
the seventh prince
of Shirone Kingdom's
imperial guard.
My name is Ginger York.
Hey, it's a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
Now, Lord Rudeus,
would you be kind enough
to accompany me
to the royal palace?
Maybe? On what business?
Pardon me. Lady Roxy
has summoned you.
Yes, absolutely,
I'll be out in a second!
[RUDEUS]
Glad that wasn't about Aisha.
What's goin' on?
[RUDEUS]
I'm going out for a bit.
[ERIS]
Sure are makin' a lotta effort.
I haven't seen
my master in a while,
so I'm kinda nervous.
[gasps] You're gonna formally
introduce me to her, right?
Yeah, of course I am!
I'll make it happen once
everything else is settled.
[RUIJERD] Are you sure
you're fine by yourself?
Oh please, you know me.
First sign of trouble,
I'll fly right back to you two.
Will you look after Aisha?
Yeah, you got it!
Good luck and be safe
out there, Rudeus!
Or don't?
[gasps]
[RUDEUS] So this is
where she's been living.
[GINGER]
Lady Roxy has told us all about
your knack for
silent spellcasting.
I'm honored to finally
meet her genius student.
[RUDEUS]
She called me a genius?
She boasts about you quite
often, as a matter of fact.
She said she felt
she wasn't qualified
to teach someone
of your caliber.
Uh, well, that's definitely
an exaggeration.
[GINGER]
This way, please.
Huh?
Okay.
[SOLDIERS] Thank you for
your dedicated service.
[RUDEUS]
Wait a sec.
You're the two guys
from yesterday, right?
[GINGER] Excuse me.
May I take your staff and bags?
Oh, yeah, thanks.
[RUDEUS] Eh, whatever.
I should focus on Roxy for now.
I mean, I haven't
seen her in seven years!
I have so much to tell her!
[GINGER]
Lord Rudeus. Um.
[RUDEUS]
Yes?
[GINGER]
Never mind. It's nothing.
This is Ginger!
I have brought the young
Lord Rudeus with me!
[PAX]
Enter!
[RUDEUS]
A man's voice? Don't tell me.
Well, now. So, this is "Rudeus."
[RUDEUS]
You're kiddin' me.
Is this portly
little pipsqueak her...?
[RUDEUS]
L-Lilia? What is this?
Where's Roxy?
[PAX]
Drop him, boys!
Ah, jeez. What the hell?
Not exactly a warm welcome.
[PAX laughs]
It's futile!
That magic circle is
a King-class barrier
I had created
specifically to trap Roxy!
A child like you has
no hope of breaking free!
And you would be?
I thought you'd never ask.
I'm Pax, seventh
prince of Shirone,
and your worst nightmare!
Is this how the throne
deals with minor offenses?
To each their own.
I'll formally apologize
for yesterday, but first,
I would ask that you
please call Roxy here.
I'm her former student
and she can confirm--
[PAX]
Roxy isn't here.
Huh?
[PAX]
Roxy isn't here!
I'm going to use you as bait
to lure her back home!
Your letter surprised me.
I never thought Roxy's lover
would dare show his face
in my domain!
W-Wait, you think I'm her lover?
Aren't you?
[RUDEUS]
Oh, thank god.
Sounds like I haven't been
cucked by this
little creep after all.
That's something, at least.
Perish the thought, sir,
that's incomprehensible!
I am but her humble and
utterly unworthy apprentice!
Well, good enough!
Roxy never did shut up
about her precious student,
so she'll definitely
come running back.
And when she does, that'll be
the end of her as a woman!
She'll live as my sex slave
to the end of her days!
She will birth my heirs!
Sorry to interrupt,
but I do have one question.
About what? Oh, yes, of course!
I'll be sure to rape her
the very first time
right before your eyes!
Then I'll pull out,
lop off your head,
and go back for round two.
I can't wait to see you both
weeping in despair!
That's great,
but I didn't hear anything
about Lilia being held captive
until after I got here.
So then, with all due respect,
how is Roxy supposed to find out
that you've captured me as well?
Idiot! Roxy is
incredibly capable,
I'm sure she'll catch
wind of it somehow!
[RUDEUS] Unless you
put the word out yourself
or let us call for help,
I don't think anybody's coming.
Shut up! Don't act so smug!
After all, you turned up,
didn't you?
I-- Well, that's because...
Meh, meh, meh, meh. I bet you
think you're pretty tough
with your wordless magic,
but you don't stand a chance
against my royal authority!
Ooh, I can't wait to
see my Roxy again!
I hope she gets here soon!
This is gonna be so much fun!
[RUDEUS]
What a moron.
[PAX] Gah. You incompetent boobs
still haven't found Aisha yet?
[GINGER] The guards
reported they destroyed
the letter she wrote.
Need we pursue her further?
[PAX] Of course, you idiot!
I want her back!
Don't you care what
happens to your family?
[GINGER] I'll dispatch
a search party at once.
[PAX]
Good! Go! Dammit!
[RUDEUS]
All right, think.
I did exactly what
the Man-God said, right?
I met Aisha just like
I did in the vision.
I used a fake name.
I wrote to Roxy.
Was this all supposed to happen?
Or did I screw up somehow?