That's great!
Congratulations, Mother!
You're such a sweetheart.
And I just know you're going to
be an excellent big brother
when this little one
comes along.
We did it, Zenith!
I'm so glad.
[PAUL] I can't believe our
little family's finally growing!
[RUDEUS] Zenith has been
worried that she couldn't
have a second child.
So, naturally, she and Paul
were overjoyed at the news.
[ALL laugh]
My humble apologies.
I'm afraid I'm pregnant.
[RUDEUS]
Time froze.
No one bothered to ask
who the father was.
Nor did anyone have to.
Forgive me, Zenith.
That child's, uh,
it's probably mine.
[RUDEUS]
Pathetic.
But, good on him for
coming clean so fast.
I suppose if he's
always going to lecture me
about "being a real man,"
that's the least he can do.
So, you know, that's gotta
count for something.
[slap]
[RUDEUS] But this is
a nightmare scenario.
[ZENITH]
So. What will you do?
After I've assisted you
with childbirth, My Lady,
I plan to take my leave of you.
[ZENITH]
And your child?
I hope to raise it
back in my hometown.
[ZENITH] That's a month's
ride south, isn't it?
Yes.
[ZENITH] You'll have to have
your baby here first.
You'll be in no
condition to travel.
Well, be that as it may.
I have nowhere else I can turn.
Zenith, s‐surely she can
just stay with u‐‐
[ZENITH]
You stay out of this!
[RUDEUS] A month of
unaccompanied travel
is a tall order for
a woman with a newborn.
This is supposed to be
a safe country,
but I still doubt they
would make it in one piece.
[RUDEUS]
And Zenith is right.
Even if Lilia has the stamina
to make it all the way there,
the odds of an infant surviving
the trip are pretty slim.
And if Lilia collapses,
they're both dead for sure.
It's not hard to imagine:
Lilia lying in the snow.
Baby cradled in her arms.
[RUDEUS]
Of course Zenith is conflicted.
Lilia has been faithful
to this house for years,
and‐‐this drama aside‐‐
they're friends.
I don't want to
lose her, either.
She brings me towels
when I train outside,
and draws baths when
I get caught in the rain.
She lays out blankets
when it's cold
and tidies up if
I leave books out.
[RUDEUS]
And most importantly.
She knows about the holy relic
and has kept it secret.
[RUDEUS]
It's time I return the favor.
Mother, I thought it
would be a good thing
that I'm gonna get two new
siblings instead of just one,
so why is everyone so upset?
[ZENITH]
It means your father and Lilia
did something very bad.
I guess I get it.
But to me it didn't
sound like Lilia
was allowed to say no to him.
What do you mean?
It kinda sounded like Father
was threatening her before.
[gasps]
Huh?
[RUDEUS] A while ago, I got up
in the middle of the night
to use the bathroom.
And when I passed Lilia's room,
I thought I heard Father
say something like,
"Spread your legs if you don't
want people to find out."
[PAUL]
Rudy! What the hell are you‐‐
I said keep your mouth shut!
[PAUL]
B‐But, hang on.
Lilia, dear. Tell me,
is that true?
The Young Master
must be mistaken.
No, forgive me.
I see you're trying
to protect yourself.
Now, hold on just a second.
I‐I never said that.
[RUDEUS] I appreciate
your help with Sylphie,
but I'll have to pay you back
for that some other time.
You kinda dug your
own grave on this one.
Sorry, Paul.
I really don't
believe that Lilia
did anything wrong, Mother.
It's all Father's fault.
I suppose.
So, it wouldn't be fair for her
to get in so much trouble
for something she
didn't do, right?
Well. No.
And you know I have a lot of fun
playing with Sylphie every day!
So don't you think
it would be nice
for the new baby
to have a friend, too?
Perhaps, yes.
And no matter what,
I'm gonna be a big brother
to both of them.
So please, Mother.
Don't make her leave.
I don't wanna say
goodbye to Lilia!
All right, Rudy.
I get it. You win.
[RUDEUS]
You didn't make it easy, Madame.
Lilia. Please stay.
You're part of the family now.
It would be foolish
to ask you to leave.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
Great. Glad that's settled.
Any further damage control
is up to you, Paul.
Sure hope you can handle it.
This is your last chance, Señor.
As for you.
I hope you're prepared
to have a nice,
long talk about all this later.
Uh...
[RUDEUS grunting]
That's way too hard!
Please stop taking
this out on me!
[LILIA]
I shouldn't have been spared.
This pregnancy is my fault.
I was the one who seduced Paul.
[PAUL, ZENITH moaning]
[LILIA] After years of
hearing them carry on
like that night after night,
I finally reached
a breaking point.
[LILIA] I'm honestly amazed
I held out this long.
[PAUL humming]
[clattering]
[PAUL gasps]
[LILIA]
I deserved to be punished.
For giving in.
For betraying Zenith.
But I was forgiven.
Rudeus made that happen.
He even guided us to
an elegant compromise.
He understood the
situation I was in
and was willing to
lie to protect me.
I've always been
frightened of that child.
So I've made a point of avoiding
him as much as possible.
[LILIA] As a baby,
he used to stare at my chest
with that repulsive grin.
It was unnerving.
I thought he might be possessed.
But it's time I let go
of that nonsense.
He saved my life, and for that,
he deserves my respect.
If this child grows up
healthy and strong,
I will see to it that
they make their way
into Lord Rudeus's service.
It's the least I can do.
Hey there, girls.
Is it Daddy or a monster?
[PAUL]
Where'd Daddy go? There he is!
[RUDEUS]
Every day with this.
Don't you have anything
better to do, Paul?
[NORN crying]
[BOTH crying]
[ZENITH gasps]
Oh dear.
You sure are a handful.
On the contrary, this is what
childrearing should feel like.
Things with Young Master
Rudeus were much too easy!
You're all right.
Darling? Would you
go draw some water?
[LILIA] Oh! And would you mind
picking up some more candles,
as long as you're out?
[PAUL]
Uh. Sure.
Sylphie. I think I
have to be the cool
male role model for those girls.
[RUDEUS]
Ever since the "incident,"
Lilia's actually
been talking to me.
Mostly old stories about Paul.
Turns out, they studied
swordsmanship
at the same training hall.
She told me he was
very talented,
but preferred to goof off.
Also, true to form,
how he'd snuck in her room
to assault and deflower
her as she slept.
And then he just bailed.
Like a dirtbag.
[PAUL] Rudy! It's time for
practice, let's get to work!
[PAUL]
Do you want to loosen up
or do you want to stay
Elementary rank forever?
[RUDEUS] Paul may be childish,
irresponsible trash,
but I don't think he's
rotten to the core.
And despite all his faults,
I respect his strength.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
There are three sword styles:
Sword God, Water God,
and North God.
Paul is Advanced in all three.
[RUDEUS gasps]
Hey, watch it, boy,
that's cheating!
[gasps]
Heh. You might have
a little talent for magic,
but your swordplay
has already stagnated.
What a shame.
Wipe that look off
your face and stand up.
Don't you want to grow up to be
a cool guy like your
old man, here?
[RUDEUS] I didn't think
it was very "cool"
to cheat on your wife and
almost rip your family apart.
If it bothers you to hear that,
would you please keep your hands
off anyone who isn't Mother?
Uh, other than Lilia, right?
I dunno, if it happens again,
Mother might move
back in with her family.
Come on, you're
a guy, you get it.
What exactly do you think
a seven‐year‐old boy
is supposed to "get"?
Well, I know you're
into little Sylphie,
and you gotta admit
that girl is gonna be
a total knockout
when she grows up.
Yeah, of course she is,
but I happen to think that
she's super beautiful already.
So you do understand.
Uh. Yeah, yeah.
[RUDEUS]
Paul's a scumbag all right,
but we speak the same language.
What am I now, forty‐something?
I was hot garbage in
my day, too. I can't judge.
By the way, Rudy.
I want to talk you about‐‐
You know what, never mind.
We should probably
get back to training.
What is it?
[PAUL] Hm? Nothing.
Just that you're at an age
where kids normally
start attending school.
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, I know.
You don't need it, though.
You can already read,
write, and do math.
[RUDEUS]
Well, yeah.
Still. I might wanna.
Are you being serious right now?
Ha. Well, don't think
too hard about it.
Joints like that are all
full of bratty nobles.
A nerdy little kid
from the sticks
would get bullied for sure.
And I'll tell ya something else,
the girls in those places
never exercised a single
day in their lives.
Sure, they look good
on the surface.
Then you get 'em into bed
with their corsets off
and they're a total mess.
Honestly I've been tricked more
times than I care to admit.
That's unfortunate.
I was kinda looking forward
to building a harem
like my dear old dad.
Hey! Would ya look at that,
you're my son after all!
But, uh, you're better off
chasing just one lady at a time.
[RUDEUS]
Yeah.
Smart and talented.
She's going to surpass me
before too long.
School, huh?
Rudy! What do you
wanna do today?
[RUDEUS sighs]
Uh?
Oh, sorry, say what?
You've been acting
weird again lately.
According to my parents, I've
been weird since I was born.
That's not what I mean.
You look sad about something.
I've been kinda stuck lately.
I haven't made any progress
with swords or magic.
But you're already
amazing, Rudy.
For my age, but I still
have a long way to go.
[SYLPHIE]
Are you gonna leave?
[RUDEUS]
I might.
I don't think this village has
much to offer me anymore.
[RUDEUS gasps]
Hey, you okay, Sylphie?
[SYLPHIE]
No. No. Please don't leave me.
I don't want you to go anywhere.
Whoa, hey. It's okay.
I understand. I'll stay
right here with you.
[RUDEUS] Yeah, why would I
ever want to leave a girl
like her behind? Just to
improve my magic? [chuckles]
What would be
so great about that?
I'd much rather live
out my days peacefully,
right here, beside her.
So, that's exactly what I'll do.
And as we grow up together,
I'll have plenty of time to make
her my ideal woman. [chuckles]
[RUDEUS]
Sylphie!
‐‐Hey. Rudy!
‐‐[RUDEUS gasps]
[chuckles]
[RUDEUS] Didn't anyone ever tell
you it's polite to knock first?
Whoa, calm down,
you've got a letter.
A letter?
[ROXY] Dear Rudeus, I hope you
and your family are well.
I can't believe
it's already been
two whole years since we parted.
[ROXY] I'm currently working
in the royal capital
of the Shirone Kingdom.
I've been hired as tutor
to the seventh prince.
[ROXY] His Highness
reminds me a bit of you.
He's not quite as talented,
but he's clever.
A budding magician
in his own right.
[ROXY] And, also like you,
he's prone to
stealing my underwear and
spying on me while I change.
They do say great men
have great lusts.
I gotcha! Oh, that's the stuff.
[PAX screams]
[ROXY] Oh! And I'm
pleased to say I finally
mastered King‐Class water magic.
I thought I'd reached my limit,
but good old‐fashioned
effort goes a long way.
I wouldn't be surprised
if you're already
casting Emperor‐Class magic.
I'm excited,
and a little nervous,
to see what you can do someday.
And I promise to work hard
to keep up with you.
I doubt I need to worry,
but if you do hit
a dead end in your studies,
I would urge you again
to seek admission
to the Ranoa
University of Magic.
Good luck! I'll write
again soon. Roxy.
Master Roxy.
So that sweet little
girl has ranked
all the way up to a Water King.
Good for her.
Is that hard to do?
Indescribably hard.
As a matter of fact,
I'd be willing to bet that
you could count all the
active King‐Class mages
in the world on one hand.
Oh, wow.
But, uh. Kiddo?
Did you really
steal her panties?
[RUDEUS]
Busted.
Talk about a wake‐up call.
Now what? Damn it.
I don't want to
disappoint my master.
Ranoa University of Magic. Huh.
Listen, Father?
May I make kind of an
unreasonable request?
You may not.
You can ask us
for anything, dear.
I'm sure your father
will manage somehow.
What a golden
opportunity to actually
demonstrate some
paternal dignity.
He wants something so crazy
that he asked permission
just to bring it up,
so I'm sure it's impossi‐‐
I'm starting to worry
that I won't improve
much more on my own.
So, I decided that
I would like to attend
the Ranoa University of Magic.
Oh yeah?
But when I brought
that up to Sylphie,
she started to cry and
begged me not to leave her.
Attaboy, I wonder
where you learned
to be such a lady‐killer.
The ideal solution would be for
the two of us
to enroll together,
but her family isn't
as well‐off as we are.
I was hoping you could
pay tuition for both of us.
So, please think about it?
Ohh. All the way to
Ranoa? Not a chance.
[PAUL] But to make sure
you understand why:
First, you're still
learning the sword.
As your teacher, I refuse
to let you quit now.
Second, you're smart,
but you're young.
It would be irresponsible of us
to send you away at your age.
Then, there's the money.
Paying for you is fine, but we
can't pay for Sylphie, too.
Got it? We're comfortable,
but we aren't nobles.
Of course not. In that case,
may I ask for
something else instead?
[PAUL]
Shoot.
[RUDEUS]
I would like to find a job.
As well‐paid as possible.
A job? What for?
By the time you decide that
I'm ready to leave home,
I hope to earn Sylphie's
tuition all by myself.
[PAUL] That might not be in
Sylphie's best interests.
[RUDEUS] Maybe not,
but I think it will be in mine.
Very well, then.
If your mind's made up,
I'll see what I can do for you.
[gasps] Thank you so much!
Good to see you, Ghislaine,
feels like it's been forever.
Idiot.
[RUDEUS]
Madam Titty Kitty!
Ghislaine, hi! I've missed you!
Have you been well?
Yeah. That your kid?
[ZENITH]
Yes! This is Norn.
[GHISLAINE] Let's hope she
doesn't take after Paul.
That's enough chit‐chat,
I assume if you're here that
means everything is ready to go.
Yeah.
Please take care of
our little Rudeus.
Can do.
[LILIA] Young Master Rudeus.
We'll miss you very much.
[RUDEUS]
Huh?
[ZENITH]
Take care, sweetheart.
We'll see you when
you get back, okay?
"Get back" from what,
I'm not going anywh‐‐
[PAUL]
Listen, Rudy.
[RUDEUS]
Yeah? What's wrong?
Tell me something.
What if I said you had to
stay away from Sylphie
for a little while?
Huh? Well, obviously
I wouldn't want to.
I figured.
Why, what's going on?
Nope. Don't even ask.
I know if I try to explain,
you'll just talk
your way out of it.
[RUDEUS]
Huh?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
That's Water God Style.
[RUDEUS sighs]
At least it's a wooden sword.
[PAUL grunts]
[gasps]
That hurt, Paul. What the hell?
[RUDEUS]
What happened?
I'm Rudeus Greyrat.
And I hope you'll
forgive my confusion.
You sure you're Paul's kid?
You seem way too polite.
My names Ghislaine.
Starting tomorrow we will
be working together.
It'll be my pleasure.
It's very nice to meet you.