[NORN]
Daddy. Daddy?
I don't know where Mommy,
Aisha, and the house are.
Where the hell are we?
[PAUL]
Zenith? Lilia? Aisha?
All right, think.
What could've caused this?
Was it that storm?
[NORN]
What's wrong?
Nothing, sweetheart.
Come on. Let's hurry home.
[GEESE humming]
[GEESE]
Hey! There you are!
[gasps] Geese, you bastard!
Where the hell have you been?
Ooh, hostile! You're as
pissy as ever, I see.
Heh.
[GEESE]
'Scuse me!
I'll take one of
whatever he's got.
[WAITRESS 17A]
You got it.
[GEESE]
Paul.
You might wanna swing by
the Guild tomorrow.
And why would I?
You might bump into
a familiar face!
Hm? Seriously, though,
what the hell
happened to you
while I was gone?
[PAUL]
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
Get real, man.
The guy I know would never
get this cranky over "nothing."
Come on, pouty pants, what's up?
You can tell me.
So that's it, is it?
I know it ain't my place,
but aren't you expecting
too much from the boy?
Huh? Really? From him?
Oh, please. Yes!
Think about it for a sec.
[GEESE] Look, I'll grant you
that Rudeus is impressive.
I mean, I've never seen anyone
cast spells without speaking.
That's what I've been saying.
He's unbelievable.
He was only five when--
I'm not done!
At the end of the day,
he's still an 11-year-old kid.
Now remind me again what is it
you were doing at that age?
Why do you care?
If I told you to survive
the Demon Continent at 11,
think you could do it?
[PAUL] Ha. Sure. Long as
I had the same handicaps.
Don't forget, he found himself
a Superd warrior bodyguard.
Anyone could have made it back
with a chaperone like that.
[GEESE]
Nope. Not a chance.
Hell, you couldn't do that now.
Ha. Doesn't that
just prove my point?
He did something
I could never do!
And that means
my boy's a genius.
So excuse me for
expecting him to
put those talents to use
from time to time.
You get that?
I'm not in the wrong here!
[GEESE sighs]
Shut up, of course you are.
But hey, what else is new, huh?
[PAUL]
What?
Tell me. You've never been to
the Demon Continent, have you?
[PAUL]
What's your point?
My point is, I grew up
in that wasteland.
[PAUL]
Huh?
And in my extremely
considered opinion,
you're taking the whole
place way too lightly.
You want to explain
what you mean by that?
I kinda have to.
You Central Continent softies
think you can
deal with anything,
but guess what, friend?
Outside of the towns,
that place is barren.
Boiling during the day.
Freezing at night.
There's no water.
There's no rain.
And you have to
hunt and kill monsters
to use them for firewood.
Monsters which, I might add,
are way stronger than
anything you ever see here.
Please, now it just sounds like
you're making stuff up.
[GEESE] He's on
his very first adventure.
He's in an unfamiliar land.
And his party includes
a Superd warrior,
for who all he knows,
could betray him at any moment.
There this teenage girl,
a hothead he's sworn
to have to protect.
And you're being
judgy that he didn't
comb the place for
survivors on top of that?
People have limits.
Especially children.
You get me?
Then riddle me this.
If it was as much of
a struggle as you say,
why would he try to
act like the whole trip
was some big, fun adventure?
Because he didn't wanna
worry dear ol' dad, obviously.
[PAUL]
Huh?
[GEESE sighs]
[PAUL] Why would he waste time
trying to protect me?
Am I that hopeless as a father?
Pretty much.
Haven't seen any evidence
to the contrary.
Ha. I guess you're right.
I mean, look at me!
Weak-willed and
drowning in booze
to ignore my own failures.
That must look real pathetic
to my little "prodigy," huh?
I don't think it takes
a prodigy to see
how pathetic you are
right now, Paul. Sorry.
[GEESE]
I pity the kid, though. I do!
After a grueling journey,
he finally reunites
with his daddy,
only to find out
the guy's turned into
a total drunken loser!
Can you imagine?
I were him?
I'd have cut ties
with you on the spot.
[GEESE] Why can't you just be
happy to see him again?
Who cares what kind
of trip he's had?
Doesn't really matter
in the grand scheme of things.
He's here now, and he's safe.
That's worth
celebrating, isn't it?
[GEESE] Unless, of course,
you would've preferred for him
to come back dead-eyed
and missing a limb or two.
[PAUL gasps]
I'm just sayin',
revisit this sober.
[VIERRA]
Captain.
Daddy...
[RUDEUS]
Whoa! She's so cute!
I can't believe
how soft her cheeks are!
Father.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
You took too long to find me.
Where were you?
I waited for so long.
Why would you
let this happen to me?
How 'bout that.
Maybe Geese was right.
[door opens]
[INNKEEPER 17A]
Hm? Come in.
[PAUL]
Uh. I-I'm...
[sighs]
What are you doing here?
I just came to talk to Rudy.
I'm his father, Paul.
[ERIS]
I know who you are!
Well how about that,
you got yourself
one devoted little lady friend!
[PAUL chuckles]
Knew I raised a playboy.
You've got some nerve
showing your face here!
Do you have any idea
what you did to hi--?
Hey, Ruijerd!
Let go of me at once!
I say we leave these two alone.
[ERIS]
You saw Rudeus last night!
That monster has
no right to speak to him!
[RUIJERD]
Don't be so harsh.
Most fathers are
far from perfect.
You're welcome to air
all your grievances.
But the only reason you can
is that your son is
still alive to hear them.
Uh. Right.
[PAUL]
Was that your new demon friend?
Yes, sir. That's Ruijerd
of the Superd tribe.
Well, he certainly seems like
a nice enough guy to me.
He doesn't terrify you?
Don't be silly. He saved my son.
[RUDEUS]
So. Can I ask why you're here?
Well, uh, you know.
I wanted to apologize.
[RUDEUS]
For what?
[PAUL]
Yesterday.
You have nothing
to be sorry for.
You were right.
I've been treating this
whole thing like a game.
It's only natural
that you'd be upset.
[RUDEUS] If anything, I should
apologize for messing around.
[PAUL]
No, no, don't say that.
I know you three probably
had it rough out there.
[RUDEUS]
Not really. I had it easy.
That so? Well, then...
[RUDEUS]
Just so we're clear,
I do feel terrible that
I never saw your message.
What did it say?
[PAUL]
It said "Forget about me.
Go search the northern
Central Continent."
[RUDEUS]
Ah.
[PAUL] Anyway, um.
What do you plan to do next?
[RUDEUS] What else?
I'm escorting Eris back home.
[PAUL]
There's nothing there anymore.
No people, no towns.
It's all grassland now.
And I hate to say it,
but there's a chance
the Boreas family is...
We'll go anyway.
[PAUL gasps]
Are you--
[RUDEUS] After that, I'll look
for Mother, Lilia, and Aisha.
[PAUL]
I see.
[INNKEEPER 17A]
This ones on me.
[RUDEUS]
Thank you very much.
Listen up, my boy.
I won't pretend
I know what's goin' on.
But you should at least
look him in the eye.
[RUDEUS] What are you
making that face for?
Heh, what face?
This is how I look.
[RUDEUS] No. I've seen that
expression somewhere before.
But when?
Oh, the mirror.
Right after I stopped going out.
[GAME CHARACTERS grunting]
[FRIEND 17A] Aw man!
You're as amazing as ever!
I guess I shouldn't
be surprised.
You basically get to spend
all day practicing. [sighs]
Must be nice, though!
Wish I could skip school.
But my dad's such a hard-ass,
he'd never let me do it.
At least not without
an excuse like yours.
Y'know?
[RUDEUS]
Cut the crap!
[FRIEND 17A]
What'd I say?
Do you think it's fun
for me to live like this?
[FRIEND 17A] Whoa, chill out!
I was just joking around, man.
Yeah, right.
Do you have any idea
what they did to me?
[RUDEUS] At the time,
I thought, "How dare you?
Look how depressed I am!
Can't you see I'm in pain?
How can you be so upbeat?
So insensitive?"
[RUDEUS] Except,
once I finally calmed down,
I realized I'd overreacted.
He'd been trying to
cheer me up, in his own way.
I decided to apologize
the next time he dropped by.
Only, he never came over again.
[RUDEUS] And I didn't
reach out to him, either.
I let my pride hold me back.
[RUDEUS]
But. Paul came back.
He went out of his way
to see me again.
Hey, Father? I have an idea.
[PAUL]
What?
It may be a challenge.
But I think we should
try to act like grown-ups.
I don't see what
you're getting at.
[RUDEUS] I'm pretty sure
he's 30 this year.
Still younger than
I was when I died.
And yet, I never took
this kind of initiative.
I just focused
on blaming others.
Compared to me,
Paul's doing great.
[RUDEUS] Let's pretend
yesterday never happened.
We didn't meet,
we didn't have a fight.
Instead, we're seeing
each other again
for the first time,
right now, in this moment.
We can start completely over.
I... What are you talking about?
[RUDEUS] But I refuse to
make the same mistakes again.
Don't overthink it!
Just come over here!
[PAUL]
Uh, 'kay.
[RUDEUS] Now, spread
your arms out. Go on!
Sure. Like this?
[RUDEUS]
Mmm. Actually, would you mind
kneeling down for me, please?
Uh, 'kay, uh, how's that?
[RUDEUS]
Father! I missed you so much!
Ru... Rudy.
[RUDEUS]
Come on.
You've been reunited
with your long-lost son.
Anything you wanna say?
[PAUL]
I missed you, too.
I missed you. I missed you.
Rudy!
[PAUL] I looked.
I couldn't find anyone.
And I... I thought
you might be dead.
I... I started picturing you,
and when I saw you...
[PAUL]
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Rudy!
[PAUL cries]
Oh, Father.
[RUDEUS] I'm sorry, too.
For everything.
[RUDEUS] And so, for the
first time in five years,
I was reunited with my father.
[RUDEUS] So, did you guys
ever have another?
[PAUL]
Nah, but not for lack of trying.
Dunno why,
we got you in one shot.
Well, I guess if you got a kid
this perfect every time,
the novelty might
eventually wear off.
[PAUL]
Ohh, you're shameless.
[BOTH laugh]
Oh hey, I'm glad you
guys are back-- Eris!
Where did that giant
bruise come from?
[RUIJERD]
I had some trouble stopping her.
[RUDEUS]
Oh.
What are you doing with him?
[PAUL]
Uh...
Well, we kinda made up.
[ERIS gasps]
How dare you?
He doesn't deserve
your forgiveness
after how he treated you!
Eris, I understand
where you're coming from,
but it's just...
Just what?
Look, everybody makes
mistakes, okay?
It's a part of
being human, you know?
[PAUL] I am deeply
sorry for the trouble
I caused the three of you.
It's fine.
If you were able to make up,
that's all that matters.
Whatever!
[RUDEUS]
Healing.
[RUDEUS] Now. I know it's
sudden, but let's go ahead
and call our second Millishion
strategy meeting to order.
Didn't we have one
like two days ago?
[RUDEUS]
Well, our situation changed.
[ERIS]
Hm?
Thanks to my father,
we don't need to
stay here any longer.
He's given us plenty
of traveling money
and a nice letter
of introduction.
Now getting to the Central
Continent will be a cinch.
H-However...
Eris. I hate to say it,
but it sounds like our homeland
doesn't really exist anymore.
[ERIS]
Oh.
And even worse,
among the missing
are Lords Phillip and Sauros.
[ERIS]
Okay.
And no one has seen or
heard from Ghislaine, either.
It's possible--
[ERIS]
Listen, Rudeus.
[gasps]
I was already prepared
for that much!
Were you really?
[RUDEUS] In that case,
I'd like to leave tomorrow.
Would that be okay with you two?
[ERIS]
Yep, no objections outta me.
[RUIJERD]
Are you sure?
Once we leave, you may never
see your father again.
True, but if we stay,
I may never see the rest of
our family again, either.
So I'd like to
make them my priority.
[RUIJERD]
I see. Makes sense.
[RUDEUS]
All right! That's everything.
You three be careful
out there, okay?
Oh, Norn. Will you come out and
say goodbye to your big brother?
Don't wanna.
[RUDEUS]
Norn.
I do look forward to
seeing you again!
We can do that, right?
[NORN]
No!
You should always
cherish your siblings.
[RUDEUS]
Well. Guess we're off.
Take care, Father.
Yeah. You, too, kid.
[GEESE] Done sayin'
yer goodbyes to the boy?
Geese! I guess I
owe you one, don't I?
Yeh, but who's keeping score?
Uh-- What's that?
Are you leaving, too?
[GEESE]
Yep. Sure am.
I combed the Great Forest,
so Begaritt is up next.
No one's looked
there yet, right?
Are you still? For me--?
[GEESE]
See ya!
Right!
Listen up, ladies.
We have an immediate
change of plans.
Round everyone up for a meeting.
[VIERRA, SHIERRA]
Yes, sir!