[RUDEUS] That little girl gave
me something truly priceless.
I can go out.
I'm done being a shut‐in.
[RUDEUS]
I won't let that go to waste.
[RUDEUS] This is the first day
of the rest of my life.
[RUDEUS]
Okay!
[PAUL]
Ohh...
Hey! Not while‐‐
[RUDEUS]
Mother! Father!
[PAUL clears throat]
May I go and play
outside for a while?
[PAUL] Outside? Well, sure.
Of course you can.
Oh, darling! Rudy is
going out on his own!
And I used to
worry he was sickly.
But time really does fly, huh?
Indeed.
Did you think something
was wrong with me?
You never cried about anything.
[RUDEUS]
That bothered you?
But I've grown up to be
so strong and charming!
Yeah, and it's
always been the ways
you don't act like a kid
that worry me the most.
[RUDEUS]
Am I not turning out to be
the firstborn son you wanted?
I mean, I'm not complaining.
[RUDEUS]
Then what?
I'm only trying to become
a more worthy heir
to the Greyrat legacy.
Ha! Well, if that's what
you want, then get out there
and bring home
a girlfriend or two.
I understand. I won't rest
until I find a woman who's
a match for dear Mother.
Aww!
Ha! Oh, and don't forget
to be kind, son.
A man should never
use his strength
to push people around.
Yeah, I know
that much, at least!
And if you've
taught me anything,
a man should use his strength
to show off to girls.
Right. Uh! No, that's not right.
[laughs] I'm just kidding.
We should use it to protect
the weak, shouldn't we?
Well. Yeah. You got
it that time.
Okay then, I'm off!
Be careful, sweetie!
He's such a wonderful boy.
I only hope I'm a good
enough father to him.
Good morning!
Hey, how's it going?
[RUDEUS] Look at this.
I'm out on my own!
I may not get to thank Roxy,
but I'll always
treasure her holy relic.
[SOMAL]
We don't want your kind here!
[CHILD 03A]
Go back to the Demon Continent!
[CHILD 03B]
And stay there!
[SOMAL]
Yeah! Get lost, demon!
[CHILD 03B]
Take this!
[RUDEUS]
Well, this feels familiar.
Knock it off!
[KIDS gasp]
What was that?
Ganging up to bully
a helpless kid?
Guys like you are the worst!
[CHILD 03B]
We're over here, idiot!
[CHILD 03A] You're the
knight's kid. Butt out!
[RUDEUS chuckles] Give it
your best shot, I'm not scared!
Where'd he get that water from?
[RUDEUS chuckles]
This is lame. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Wow.
[RUDEUS]
Holy crap. This kid's a looker.
He's gonna be a total chick
magnet here in a few years.
[SYLPH]
Uh. Yeah. I'm all right.
Hey, lean forward
for just a second.
Uh. 'Kay.
[RUDEUS] He's pretty cooperative
when he's not being screamed at.
Calling it now, he's gonna
be a dude magnet, too.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
Hey! Close your eyes.
You'll have to wash
your clothes at home.
There. All done.
[SYLPH]
Th‐Thank you.
[ROXY] They're fairly
easy to recognize:
they all have emerald green hair
and red gems in their foreheads.
So don't you dare go
anywhere near them.
[RUDEUS] His forehead
is smooth and white.
Okay, safe. He's not one of
those dangerous Superds.
But, those ears.
[RUDEUS] You know,
kids like that won't stop
unless you learn to fight back.
Are... Are you sure
the way I look
doesn't scare you or anything?
No way, my master was Migurdian.
Are you a demon, too?
I'm not sure.
My dad says that I'm not.
[RUDEUS] He doesn't know?
At his age? That's odd.
Mom's human. My dad's half elf.
[RUDEUS] Nice, I knew it!
Of course this world has elves!
But my hair color isn't the same
as either of my parents.
[cries]
Huh? Wait, please
don't cry! There, there.
[RUDEUS] Sounds like his home
life is a little complicated.
But no one should
get pelted with mud
just for their hair color.
[RUDEUS] Just thinking
about it pisses me off.
[SYLPH]
Um. Why did you help me?
[RUDEUS]
My father always told me that
I should be an ally to the weak.
[SYLPH] But the other kids
might not like you now.
I'd rather play with you
than a bunch of bullies.
Huh?
We are friends now, aren't we?
[gasps]
[RUDEUS] Unless you're too busy
with chores or something?
[SYLPH]
Mm‐mm!
[RUDEUS chuckles]
[RUDEUS]
This guy.
A little more confidence and
the girls will be all over him.
A few might even come
my way if we stick together.
You know, I never
introduced myself!
My name is Rudeus. And you?
It's Sylph.
[RUDEUS]
Sylph? That's a cool name!
You're like a wind spirit!
Yeah.
[RUDEUS giggles]
[RUDEUS] Woohoo!
What do you want to play?
I don't know.
I've never played
with a friend before.
[RUDEUS] Yeah, I guess he's
never really had one, huh?
I feel bad for him.
Though, I don't really
have friends, either.
That trick you
did before. Do it again.
Trick?
Like when you made warm water
go all sploosh from your hands,
and then you made
that woosh of hot air.
Oh. Magic.
[SYLPH]
Can I do it, too?
[RUDEUS] Sure, if you learn
the right incantations. I think.
"Incantations"?
Do you want to?
Uh‐‐
Okay! Then we'll start
your training right away.
[RUDEUS]
I'm home, Father!
Father?
[PAUL] Do you know why
I'm upset with you?
[RUDEUS] Nope. Is this about
Roxy's panti‐‐ holy relic?
Uh, no sir, I don't.
Interesting.
I hear you punched
Ms. Eto's boy Somal today.
[RUDEUS sighs]
My stash is safe. Wait, what?
Did you say today?
[PAUL]
I did.
[RUDEUS]
Aha. I gotcha.
Must be the brat
who was bullying Sylph.
I'm not sure what
you heard, Father,
but I promise you‐‐
Enough! When you do
something wrong,
you apologize first!
I was playing by myself
and I heard voices‐‐
[PAUL]
No excuses!
[RUDEUS]
His mind's made up,
and he has no intention
of hearing me out.
[PAUL]
What's that look for?
[RUDEUS] I could apologize
and get it over with,
but I don't think that
would be best for Paul.
Well then? Why won't
you say anything?
[RUDEUS] Because you'll just
yell at me to not make excuses.
What?
You want to shout
and make me apologize
before I can explain?
Must be nice to lord that
kind of power over a kid.
Rudy!
[slap]
[RUDEUS] Father. I have always
put in the utmost effort
to be a good son
to you and Mother.
Well, that's beside the point.
No, it isn't.
I've worked hard
to earn your trust,
and you took
someone else's word.
You yelled at me,
you raised your hand to me,
and still you refuse to listen.
And? You injured little Somal!
I won't apologize
even if that is my fault.
I'm proud of what I did today.
Wait, hang on.
Tell me what happened.
I thought you
told me "no excuses."
But please don't worry
about it, Father.
The next time I see three
kids ganging up on someone
who won't fight back,
I'll simply ignore it.
In fact, I'll even
jump in myself
and make it four against one.
I'll be sure to
let everyone know
that that's the
Greyrat family way.
But once I grow up
and leave home,
I'll never use
the Greyrat name again.
I'll be too ashamed
to belong to a family
that ignores violence
and accepts verbal abuse.
[RUDEUS]
You'd better take the L, Paul.
I know you can't tell,
but I spent two decades
weaseling my way out of
unwinnable arguments.
And this time,
I'm completely in the right.
You haven't got a chance.
[PAUL]
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Tell me what happened.
[RUDEUS]
Hi, Mother!
[ZENITH] Welcome back, Rudy.
Did you have fun today?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, I made a new friend.
[ZENITH]
You did? How wonderful!
[PAUL]
That could have gone better.
I expect you to
give that son...
[PAUL] Somal did have
one heck of a black eye.
Just look at what he did!
[PAUL]
Rudeus matured so quickly.
I was almost relieved to hear
he'd done something so childish.
Even so. He's already a
Saint‐Class water mage.
Of course he would have trouble
relating with the other kids.
I only meant to
scold him a little.
Where did I go wrong?
How stupid.
I want to show him
those with power
shouldn't resort
to violence, and yet...
What's the matter?
You look gloomy.
[PAUL] Mm. Ah. I had a little
fight with Rudy earlier.
That's not like you.
I was this close to
telling him to leave.
I bet he would have done it
without a second thought.
Just like that.
You mean like you did?
[PAUL chuckles]
[PAUL] I wonder if
this is how my dad felt.
I wish I'd gotten to apologize.
[RUDEUS]
And it's summer again.
Those bratty kids kept
coming after me and
Sylph for a while,
but they're pretty
easy to take care of.
That one mom keeps
showing up to complain.
But, if we're being
honest, I think she's
more interested in Paul
than her kid's wellbeing.
She just wants an excuse
to come see him. Stupid.
[sighs] Why is it so hot?
It sucks out here.
I'm sorry. Am I late?
Nope! I just got here.
[RUDEUS]
I didn't.
I did it!
[RUDEUS]
Sylph's mana has grown a lot
in the past six months.
He can train for hours
at a time now.
So I guess the idea
that there are limits
on a person's magical
reserves is total bunk.
Hey! I wanna learn
that one you did
where you made a warm breeze!
Oh, that?
For that one, you conjure water,
and then apply fire to it.
You didn't even have to
say anything out loud.
[RUDEUS]
Hm? Silent spellcasting.
I think it might be kind of
hard for a beginner.
So? Show me how.
[RUDEUS]
Let me think.
[RUDEUS sighs]
Okay.
You know how when you
say an incantation,
you feel all your
mana rush through
your body into your fingertips?
[SYLPH]
Mm.
[RUDEUS] You gotta focus on that
feeling for a specific spell,
but then recreate it
without saying the words.
Does that make sense?
Try it with an easy one.
[SYLPH]
'Kay!
[SYLPH grunting]
[RUDEUS] It's hard to
teach something you do
by feeling alone.
Even Roxy couldn't do it.
Maybe wordless casting
really is special.
Actually, I kinda hope it is.
I had nothing going
for me in my old life.
Would a convenient skill or two
be too much to ask for?
[SYLPH] I did it!
Rudy, did you see that?
[SYLPH giggles]
I did it! I did it!
Way to go!
[SYLPH giggles]
I did it! I figured it out!
Hey, Sylph! Wait up!
Sylph, come on!
[sighs]
[RUDEUS sighs]
[RUDEUS]
He really is a looker.
Even a dude like me can see it.
Dammit. I'm jealous.
The old me had a friend
like this in junior high,
but "she" was a "girl."
She wasn't into me, but I
thought about her all the time.
Even after I found out
she'd got married,
I could still punch my clown
about three times a day
to the ol'
"childhood friend" trope.
[RUDEUS]
Hurry up, Sylph!
Hey, I'm back.
There you are. Welcome home.
Young Master and... friend?
Nice to meet you.
I've drawn a bath for you.
Great. Thank you.
Follow me, Sylph!
[SYLPH]
O‐Okay.
Perfect. What's the matter?
[RUDEUS] You'll get cold
standing around like that.
Uh, yeah.
Then get undressed and hop in.
Uh, 'kay.
[RUDEUS]
Come on, now.
[SYLPH gasps]
You're old enough
to do this yourself.
[SYLPH gasping]
I don't know what you're
so embarrassed for.
But these gotta come off, too.
[SYLPH gasps]
No. Please don't.
I'm serious,
you're gonna get sick.
Just do it.
Cut it out!
[RUDEUS] Trust me, bud,
I know exactly how you feel.
The old me wouldn't wanna bathe
with other dudes, either.
Welcome to the weird
dick club, champ.
I promise I won't laugh at you.
That's not what I... Rudy, no!
[RUDEUS] What the hell's this
kid got going on down there?
[RUDEUS]
You kidding me with this?
Don't make me get naked alone.
[RUDEUS] All right, fine.
Bathe like that.
But you're gonna have to
change at some point.
‐‐[RUDEUS] Unless I do this!
‐‐[RUDEUS] Gotcha!
[SYLPH gasps]
[SYLPH screams]
[RUDEUS] What flashed before
my eyes in that moment
was not the pure short sword
I've grown accustomed to.
Now, it wasn't some dark blade
covered in sinister
designs, either.
What should have
been there, simply wasn't.
And what was there
stunned me to my core.
In my old life, I'd only
ever seen one on my monitor
while I was "taming
the beast," so to speak.
And then I realized what I'd
just done was not okay at all.
He was a she.
I think we should talk about
what just happened.
I'm sorry.
[PAUL] I won't fly off
the handle this time.
I refuse to make
that mistake twice.
Just tell me why
you did it, kid.
We were wet from the rain.
I thought she was
gonna catch a cold.
[PAUL]
But, she said "no," didn't she?
Yes. I'm sorry.
This is only going to get
more important as you grow up,
so I need you to
pay close attention.
You have to be respectful.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Don't say that to me.
Go apologize
to Sylphiette. Okay?
Sylphiette? Of course.
Is she ever gonna forgive me?
[PAUL chuckles]
Ah, don't you worry.
As long as you apologize
sincerely, I'm sure she will.
[PAUL] I know how it feels when
the girl you like rejects you.
It seems my particular fondness
for women runs in the family.
But you're such
a smart boy, my son.
I know you'll learn a lot
from this failure.
[PAUL] I still worry about you,
but I'm so hopeful.
I'm sorry, Sylphiette!
Your hair is really short,
so I actually thought you were
a boy this whole time!
[ALL gasp]
‐‐[ZENITH gasps]
‐‐[SYLPHIE cries]
[ZENITH]
Oh, goodness.
[RUDEUS gasps]
[PAUL] On second thought,
my son might be a total idiot.
[grunts]
[RUDEUS pants]
[laughs] Not your
best effort, kid!
Are you still having trouble
making up with Sylphiette,
or is it somethin' else?
Yeah. She's still upset
and my swordsmanship
hasn't improved, either.
You want some friendly
advice from your old man?
Absolutely.
Uhh, I don't know.
Shall I lick your boots?
Eager, are we?
Listen, Rudy.
Women like our strength,
but sometimes it's
important to show them
our softer aspects as well.
Ohh.
Think for a second: If someone
clearly stronger than you
were to chase after
you with naked lust,
how would that
make you feel, son?
I guess I'd be scared?
Of course. So show her
your vulnerable side instead.
I get it! But where do I start?
Next time you see Sylphiette,
be honest with her about all
the feelings you've bottled up.
Let her know how much
you miss her
or that you're worried
she's been avoiding you.
After that, it's all up to her.
But if it goes well,
she might even console you.
[RUDEUS gasps] So what do I do
if it doesn't go well?
You come right back to me
and I'll tell you
what the next move is.
Whoa. That's so cool!
You've got backup plans
and everything!
You know it! Now.
[RUDEUS gasps]
[PAUL]
Get going!
Listen, about before.
[RUDEUS panting]
Are you okay? Rudy?
I... I was just thinking
that I haven't seen
your c‐cute face
around here lately,
and that's a real
shame, you know?
Yeah! 'Cause you're,
like, really cute,
and your hair is pretty,
so have you thought
about growing it out?
Huh? Not really.
[RUDEUS gasps]
I'm afraid you don't
like me anymore, Sylphie.
[gasps]
I'm sorry. But you're wrong.
I promise I don't hate you
or anything, Rudy.
Are you sure?
Can we just go back to normal?
[RUDEUS]
A cute, kind girl my own age.
I have no idea how to be friends
with someone like her.
And now that I know
she's a girl,
it's hard not to
think about the future.
But she wants our relationship
to stay exactly the same.
[RUDEUS] So, I won't
think too hard about it.
And to the best of my ability,
I'm going to cherish my first
real friend in this new world.
[ALL laughing]
Hang on.
What in the hell did I just
teach my six‐year‐old son?