Wait! Don't leave without me!
[gasps]
Are you all right?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah.
[RUIJERD]
Who is the "Man-God"?
[RUIJERD] The Man-God
and the Dragon God.
Two of the Seven Gods of old.
Hard to believe they're
still fighting in this age.
You should also know,
the Superd's poor reputation
is actually due to a curse.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS] Laplace transferred
his own curse to his spears,
and when he gifted
those to the Superd...
[gasps]
[sighs] Then I suppose
everything we've done
has been for naught.
But the Man-God did say,
unlike most curses,
this one is fading.
[RUIJERD]
What?
You still carry a bit of it,
but cutting your hair helped.
Is that true?
[ERIS groans]
[RUDEUS gasps]
[RUDEUS] Mm-hm.
What remains now is mostly
just deep-seated prejudice,
but with hard work,
that'll fade, too.
All right.
That's quite a relief.
Well. I should prob'ly
get back to sleep.
Of course.
What are you working on?
I was hoping I could figure out
one of the spells that
Orsted used against me.
Why, what did he do with it?
[RUDEUS]
He nullified all of my spells.
[ERIS]
Oh, so, why are you...?
[RUDEUS]
Research, mostly.
If we ever run into
Orsted again,
I want to know I can
at least get away from him.
[PAUL] Aw, you done?
That can't be all you got!
[LILIA] Master Rudeus, would you
hang that one up, please?
[RUDEUS]
Okay!
That's much better!
Keep up the good work!
Thank you!
[ZENITH hums]
Welcome home, sweetheart!
Mother! I made
a new friend today!
[gasps]
[RUDEUS, SYLPHIETTE giggling]
[SYLPHIETTE]
Rudy! Wait for me!
[RUDEUS] Nope! You gotta
hurry up, Sylphie!
[RUIJERD]
So, this is your homeland.
It is, but you'll have to
take my word for it
that it used to be
much more beautiful.
Understood.
I wish I'd seen it then.
[RUIJERD] Well, this is
where I take my leave.
Huh?
[gasps]
I am in your debt.
For what? I didn't do anything.
Not on the Demon
Continent or Millis.
[RUIJERD]
That's not true.
You taught me that I have
so many more options
than I had ever considered
or even realized.
And I'll never forget
a second of it.
The adventurers at
the Guild in Rikarisu
smiling at the name "Dead End"
without even a hint of fear.
The closeness I felt
with the Doldia,
who accepted me
regardless of my tribe.
The Shirone soldiers
who tearfully thanked me
for helping to
rescue their families.
That had nothing to do with me.
You did all that yourself.
No, sir.
I couldn't achieve
anything on my own.
Four hundred years since the war
and I didn't advance
a single step.
Until I met you, Rudeus.
Maybe, but that's still only
because of the Man-God's adv--
I care nothing for the words
of a god I've never seen.
The one who actually helped me
along was you and you alone.
You hear me?
Eris.
Yeah, what?
You have incredible talent.
Enough to become
far, far stronger
than I could ever hope to be.
Whatever. You're lying.
You rushed in headfirst
against a powerful god
and you're still standing.
You must realize
what that means.
Of course I do!
Good. Good girl.
[RUIJERD] Would it be all right
if I treated you two
as children for
this one last moment?
[gasps]
I suppose it's time
I returned this to you.
You know. Actually, I'd prefer
that you hung on to it.
Are you sure?
I thought this was
a prized possession.
Yeah, that's why
I want you to have it.
All right, then. Rudeus. Eris.
We will meet again.
[RUDEUS]
There's so much I want to say.
And there's so much more
that I couldn't possibly
put into words.
I just... don't want to
say goodbye. Not yet.
[RUDEUS] But he's right.
We will meet again. Someday.
[VILLAGER 22A crying]
[ERIS gasps]
Ghislaine!
[gasps] Eris!
At last. Lady Eris.
I'm so glad you're safe!
There she is.
Master Rudeus. Welcome home.
I'm delighted to see
your safe return, Lady Eris.
And yours, young master.
[ERIS] You're both all right.
I'm so happy.
[ALPHONSE] Master Rudeus, if you
would please wait outside.
Huh? Yes. Of course.
[ERIS]
No! Rudeus stays with me.
If that is what you wish,
My Lady, then so it shall be.
On behalf of the Boreas House,
we're glad you've returned.
Skip the formalities.
Just say it.
Who's dead?
With great sadness,
I must say we've
lost Lord Philip,
Lady Hilda, and Lord Sauros.
[gasps]
[ERIS]
And you're sure of this?
[ALPHONSE]
Lord Philip and Lady Hilda
were teleported together
and passed away somewhere
in the Conflict Zone.
Ghislaine confirmed
this herself.
And my grandfather?
He was held responsible
for the mana disaster,
and executed.
[gasps] That's absurd!
How can you hold
somebody responsible
for a natural disaster?
[ERIS]
Rudeus. Sit back down.
[ALPHONSE] I understand
how you feel, Master Rudeus,
but I am afraid this is
the current state
of the Asura Kingdom.
In that case, what happens now?
[ALPHONSE] Lord Pilemon
Notos Greyrat wishes to
take you as his concubine,
My Lady, an arrangement...
[GHISLAINE]
Alphonse!
Are you seriously considering
that scumbag's offer?
Scum or not, he is a lord.
I don't care what his title is!
Are you thinking about
Eris' feelings at all?
I am thinking about
the Boreas family legacy
and the continued
prosperity of the people
of the Fittoa region.
[GHISLAINE] And you intend to
sacrifice her for that?
Yes, if necessary.
Eris, you don't have
to do a thing he says,
do you understand?
You can run away and be happy!
And what will become
of the people?
You do something for them!
Shut up!
Go away. I want to think.
Eris. Listen.
Did you not hear me?
I want to be alone.
I'll go then.
[ERIS crying]
[RUDEUS]
What's that?
[GHISLAINE]
The list of the missing.
So, uh, my mother still
hasn't been found yet?
[GHISLAINE]
No.
[RUDEUS gasps]
Sylphie? It can't be!
[GHISLAINE]
Someone you know?
It is.
[GHISLAINE] Did you check
the list of the dead?
[gasps]
She's not there.
Then she's probably still alive,
although I couldn't
tell you where.
Oh, thank god.
[ERIS]
Are you awake?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, come in.
Hi, Rudeus. Good evening.
Hey, Eris. Are you
feeling better?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I mean, I kind of figured this
is how things would end up.
So what do you think
you're gonna do?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, about what
Alphonse was suggesting earlier.
Who cares about all that?
I kinda figured you might.
Rudeus. I'm left
all by myself now.
And, you know.
I turned 15
not too long ago.
[RUDEUS gasps] I'm so sorry,
it completely slipped my mind!
I, um... I could still
get a present for you,
if it's not too late.
Is there anything
that you might want?
A family.
Rudeus, I... I want
you to be my family.
Do you mean we'd be
like brother and sister?
[ERIS]
No, I don't.
Whatever you wanna call it,
what I'm trying to say is,
I want to sleep together.
[RUDEUS]
Isn't that a little sudden?
[ERIS]
We promised, remember?
[RUDEUS] Yeah, but I thought we
promised for when I turned 15.
I don't really care either way.
[RUDEUS] I do!
What the hell is going on?
Okay, think.
Eris is feeling hopeless.
She wants comfort.
And I mean, yeah,
I wanna do it, but now?
Wouldn't I be taking
advantage of her?
[ERIS]
Well?
[RUDEUS]
Uh-- Hey! Eris, wait!
Well, well. What's this?
[RUDEUS]
It's 'cause you're cute.
[ERIS] That means you're
turned on right now?
[RUDEUS]
Yes.
[ERIS]
So you do like me, then?
[RUDEUS]
Yes.
[ERIS]
And you want this, too?
[RUDEUS]
Yes.
[ERIS]
But you're still saying no?
I'm sorry,
a promise is a promise.
We said we'd wait 'til I'm 15.
How 'bout this, then.
I'm gonna say something
my mother taught me.
But it's embarrassing,
so I'm only gonna say it once.
Rudeus, listen close.
I want to be your
little kitty, meow.
[RUDEUS]
Good morning, everyone!
Or, rather, great morning!
Wonderful morning!
Ah, don't look so glum!
You look like a man who needs
to get some "experience"!
It'll put a smile on your face,
I guarantee it!
And to all you
non-virgins out there:
as of today, I'm one of you!
I'm a normie now! I've made it!
Oh, my! Would you
look at the time?
If you'll excuse me.
I've got plans
with my girlfriend!
Wakey wakey, Eris! It's morning!
Time to have some fun!
Eh-- She's not here.
Ah, she must be
embarrassed! Silly girl.
[RUDEUS]
Huh?
Is this her hair...?
[ERIS] Rudeus. You and I aren't
well-matched right now.
I'm going away.
Alphonse, where is Eris?
Ahh, she's set out on
a journey with Ghislaine.
Wh-Where to?
[ALPHONSE] My apologies,
but she specifically
instructed me not to inform you.
Oh. I...
Is that so?
[RUDEUS]
But... Why?
I don't get it.
So. Did she dump me?
Abandon me?
And what about "family"?
[RUDEUS sobbing]