[CLIFF crying]
And there you are! See?
[meows]
Huh?
[gasps]
[DEMON 24A] Explain to me
why we're the only ones
who have to pay
such a huge toll!
It doesn't make sense!
Sorry, but if you want in,
you have to pay.
[TEMPLE KNIGHT 24A]
You there. Demons.
Drop your weapons.
[DEMON 24A groans]
[OFFICIAL 24A]
All right. Next.
[gasps]
I want that goblin-slaying
quest! Is it still open?
Yes! Exterminating goblins pays
one Millis bronze
piece per head.
You only need to preserve
the left ear of each
goblin as proof,
and you can turn
them in right here
at the counter to
collect your reward.
Sounds good to me!
[CLIFF]
But why?
Give me one good reason
I can't join your party!
I already told you,
you're not the right rank, kid.
Huh?
[CLIFF]
I said a good reason.
Why does rank matter
when I'm just as strong as
any A-ranked magician?
You should be grateful
I'm willing to
work with the likes of you!
Say what? You brat,
you really wanna
pick a fight at
point-blank range?
[CLIFF] Hmph. Of course,
all you can do is swing a sword.
And I am generously
offering my help,
which you clearly need!
You little shit stain!
That's an awful lot of
big talk you're spewin'.
I hope you're ready
to back it up.
C'mon. Why don't you
show us some of that
"A-ranked" power of yours, huh?
[ERIS] That's enough.
You're being childish.
Coulda sworn this
was a Guild hall,
not a daycare. Let's go.
Well, it's certainly
a good thing I was here!
Nobody asked you to
butt in and settle things!
[CLIFF] I could have
handled those thugs
just fine with my magic!
So just keep your ugly nose
out of other people's
business! Got it?
[ERIS grunts]
[CLIFF groans]
[thud]
[ERIS] Who are you calling ugly,
you little twerp?
Say that one more time,
I dare you!
Here! I'll even give you
a closer look!
[CLIFF]
Wait!
Please wait!
I'm really sorry for
what I said earlier!
It was just a heat of
the moment thing.
Uh, my name's Cliff!
Cliff Grimoire!
I'm Eris.
Eris, huh? What a
truly lovely name!
By your dress,
you're a swordswoman?
The strength in that
punch gave me chills!
I'd be most honored if you
would form a party with me!
[ERIS]
Not a chance.
[CLIFF] Well, in that case,
at least allow me
to support you from the rear.
I'm quite often described as
a budding sage, you know.
I promise I'll be helpful!
You being a better mage
than Ruedeus is unlikely.
You may be well-traveled,
but I highly doubt you've ever
seen a mage of my caliber.
I may not look it,
but I can already outperform
your average A-rank.
Huh?
[CLIFF] You owe it to yourself
to at least see what I can do!
All right, fine.
If you're that insistent,
then follow me.
[gasps] Okay!
[GOBLIN 24A groans]
I invoke the spirit
of the disruptor,
darkest devil and
prince of flame!
Rise now from
the depths of hell!
Raise thy fist aloft!
Slay, incinerate and
devour my sworn foes
to sate thy bloodlust.
Dye them black!
Exodus Flame!
[GOBLINS gasp]
[CLIFF]
Well? How do you like that?
Your average magician
could never pull that one off!
[ERIS]
Really? Can't say I'm impressed.
[CLIFF]
It sounds like you don't know
very much about magic, then.
Let me assist.
Magic is divided into ranks from
Elementary to Emperor.
With reasonable diligence,
any decent mage
can master Intermediate-level
spells. However!
The spell I just cast
is an Advanced-level.
And most adults can't even
handle an Exodus Flame.
That's right!
Only a fraction of
all mages have ever
mastered Advanced spellcasting!
So I ask again.
Now do you realize
how amazing I a--
[ERIS]
Okay, I've seen enough.
You're not gonna be much help,
so you can leave now.
You should really reconsider.
You were struggling to
kill a handful of goblins!
I can't leave you
out here alone!
Hey, what was that for?
Whatever, forget it,
let this divine power
be rich and nourishing,
offering those
whose strength has
been lost the strength
to rise again.
Healing.
[CLIFF]
Fine. I get it now.
You've made your point, Eris.
You're obviously very strong.
[CLIFF] Hm. How about we head
into the forest for a while?
I can't demonstrate my true
worth fighting mere goblins.
No, it's dangerous.
Not to mention night will fall
long before we get back.
Eris, surely you're
not scared. Are you?
Of course I'm not scared!
Fine! Let's get going!
[ERIS gasps]
Something I can help you with?
Yeah, are you keeping track
of a path out of here?
Not really, no.
[ERIS]
Well. We're lost, then!
Huh?
So what should we do?
[ERIS] Shoot yourself up
into the air for a second
and see which way the city is.
Don't be ridiculous.
I can't do something like that.
Yeah? Well Rudeus could.
Right, okay. And he would be?
[ERIS]
He's my tutor.
O-Oh.
[gasps]
Uh. Eris, what was that?
[ERIS] There must be other
adventurers in this forest.
[CLIFF gasps]
Of course!
We can just ask them for help!
Let's try to find them. Eris?
[ERIS]
Shh.
This way. Come on!
[CLIFF] Come where?
Wait! What'd you find?
People. Someone's
fighting over here.
How do you know?
[ERIS]
I can sense their presence.
Did you learn that
from your teacher?
[ERIS]
I did!
Then this "Rudeus" must be
a truly incredible person.
He is! Rudeus is amazing!
--[ERIS gasps]
--Huh?
[ERIS]
Get down!
[gasps] Eris, that's the armor
of the Temple Knights!
[THERESE]
You fools!
Surely you know who
this young lady is!
[ASSASSIN 24A]
Of course.
[THERESE]
Then why seek to harm her?
[ASSASSIN 24A]
Is it not obvious?
[THERESE]
I see. You serve the pope!
[gasps] Hey, please don't
do anything crazy.
We can't get mixed up in this!
That's the Blessed Child being
used to challenge the papacy.
Which means those men
in black attacking her
are the current pope's
personal assassins!
They're ruthless.
Not even I would stand
a chance against them!
I just hope they don't see us.
So stay quiet.
[ERIS]
Too late. They already have.
[CLIFF]
Huh?
[inhales, exhales]
[ERIS] I want you to
stay here and stay hidden.
Eris!
Too slow!
[ASSASSIN 24C groans]
[ASSASSIN 24D grunts]
[THERESE]
Watch yourself!
Their daggers are
dipped in poison!
[ASSASSIN 24D groans]
[ASSASSIN 24E]
You go on ahead.
[gasps]
[ASSASSIN 24E yells]
[ASSASSIN 24E groans]
One got away.
Sorry I couldn't get 'im.
[THERESE] My sincerest thanks
for your assistance.
[ERIS]
I'm just glad the child is safe.
My name is Therese Latria.
I'm a member of
the Temple Knights.
May I ask your name?
Are you an adventurer
from the local guild?
Yeah, I'm Eri--
I'm Ruijerd of
the party Dead End!
Believe it or not,
I'm actually a Superd!
A Superd?
[ERIS]
Hm?
[gasps] Are you really?
Very well, I understand.
Oh. And come to think of it,
I'm also pretty lost.
As thanks for saving you,
can you show me
the way back to town?
Of course! What manner
of knight would I be
if I declined to escort
our brave rescuer?
[THERESE whistles]
All right. Shall we be off?
[CLIFF]
Wait for me! I'm here, too!
[ERIS]
What are you wearing that for?
[CLIFF]
This old thing?
Uh. Please pay it no mind.
If you say so. Come on.
[CLIFF]
Right!
[ASSASSIN 24E]
Master Cliff...
What are you doing
with a Temple Knight?
[RUIJERD]
Tell me something.
Why did you target a child?
Who's asking?
Ruijerd of the party Dead End.
I've heard of you.
What would possess you
to side with their faction?
They want to drive
all demons out of Millis.
I'm not with them.
I see. You should join us.
The reigning pope wishes for us
all to coexist with demonkind.
[BLESSED CHILD 24A]
Thank you, Miss! Goodbye!
Be careful on
your way home, okay?
Welp. That was fun,
but I guess this is
where we part ways.
[CLIFF]
Miss Eris.
Will you marry me?
Absolutely not!
Huh?
You've gotta be kidding me!
How can you refuse someone
so profoundly talented?
Don't tell me that you and--
and that teacher of yours are...
What sort of person is
this man Rudeus, anyway?
Rudeus is amazing!
He can cast spells
without saying anything!
Silent casting?
Hmph. That's impossible,
no one can do that.
And even if he could,
it would surely stunt
his mastery of the craft!
[ERIS] He knows more
spells than you do!
[ERIS]
Rudeus became a Saint-class
water mage when he was five,
and he did it all
with wordless magic!
He's smaller than me,
but he beat a North Saint
on his own the other day!
Well, I only heard
about that later.
I didn't actually see him do it.
But I'm sure he took him
out in no time flat!
I mean, he is Rudeus after all.
[CLIFF] Whatever. I could
prob'ly do that, too.
[CLIFF gasps]
[inaudible]
[CLIFF]
I should head home.
[ERIS]
Okay. Bye.
[gasps] Hey, Ruijerd!
What have you been
doin' all day?
I had an errand to run.
That's cool!
You wanna know what I did?
I went out to slay
some goblins, right,
and I met this lady
in the forest
trying to protect a little girl!
A bunch of weirdos
had them hemmed in,
but I swooped in to help
and totally saved the day!
[MAID 24A]
Master Cliff!
I'm terribly sorry to be
the bearer of bad news, sir,
but I've just received word.
Four of your esteemed tutors
have fallen in battle.
Rumor has it that they fell prey
to a band of wandering demons.
I'm afraid this
will make conflict
with the archbishop's
supporters inevitable.
I'm back, Rudeus!
Get a load of this!
After I was done
slaying goblins, I got...
[ERIS gasps] Who was it?
Who did this to you?
[RUDEUS]
I'm fine.
You're obviously not!
Rudeus, huh.
'Kay.