[ELINALISE] It reeks
of sweat and pheromones.
How simply marvelous!
Don't you think, Talhand?
No, but your shamelessness
is so brazen it's
almost refreshing.
[ROXY] Elinalise,
we're not here for you
to find a man, remember?
Yeah, yeah,
Paul's family, I got it.
But we have time
for a little fun.
[sighs] And what, pray tell,
does she expect us to do
if she winds up pregnant
by the time we leave town?
Look at that!
It seems you're
fairly popular with
the younger ones in
your own right, Roxy!
Not in that way.
And even if I was,
I don't have the time
to waste on romance right now.
[ROXY]
Uh, hey.
[ALL laughing]
[ROXY]
Would you please knock it off?
[ROXY] It just occurred to me
that I've never asked.
You were both members of
the Fangs of the
Black Wolf, right?
What were Paul and
Zenith like back then?
Paul was scum.
Walking garbage.
[ROXY]
Really?
[ELINALISE]
If it's all the same to you,
I'd rather not discuss the man.
[ROXY]
And yet, you're both out here
helping me look for him.
Sounds like you care
far more than you let on.
Still. What in the world
could he have done
for a reaction like that?
[ROXY]
Dead End.
There's not a soul alive
on this continent
that doesn't know
that devil's name.
He's especially dangerous,
even for a Superd.
And as the name implies,
it's said that
none who cross his path have
ever lived to tell the tale.
You already lost me.
I thought that was a party name.
Can you keep up with
the discussion for
more than 15 seconds at a time?
Dead End is a real person!
And it seems
a party of adventurers
has been using that name
ever since the mana disaster.
So that's who we've been
hearing about all day.
But I don't think
it's a coincidence.
Well, I know which one
I'd like to question.
Give me that tall, fair spearman
who wears a permanent scowl.
I could take him to bed
and get plenty out of him.
Same priorities as ever.
I at least learned
their party dynamics.
"Mad Dog Eris" is
a red-haired swordsman
with a furious blade and temper.
"Guard Dog Ruijerd"
loves children
and never turns
a blind eye to evil.
And their leader,
"Kennel Master Rudyjerd,"
is a tiny little mage who's
perpetually up to no good.
Their reputation as
a whole isn't great,
but they say
the Guard Dog's all right.
Now that's interesting.
Superd are usually
melee fighters, not mages.
And they don't have red hair,
much less a sense of justice.
In any case, I think
we should take care
to give them
a fairly wide berth.
If even one of them
is the real Dead End,
getting too involved
with them would be suicide.
[TALHAND] Aye. We don't need to
draw attention from riffraff
like that when we're
tryin' to help folks.
[ROXY]
Speaking of which, we need to
touch base on the main mission.
Did you pick up on
any leads or rumors
about the Fittoa
displacement survivors?
[TALHAND]
Not a one.
[ELINALISE]
Total wash on anything useful.
It's been a year
since they teleported.
I wonder if we're just
too late to save them.
Although, we are talking
about the Greyrats, here,
so they should be okay!
Zenith, yes.
Lilia, Aisha,
and Rudeus, though.
I'm not so sure.
Zenith can handle stuff
like this in her sleep.
She may have long since retired,
but she was an S-ranked cleric.
And Rudeus stands out,
so he should be easy to find,
provided he's alive.
So I guess we should focus
our efforts on Lilia and Aisha.
Sounds like a plan.
I'll set out in the morning
to search for intel.
As will I.
[ROXY] I appreciate that
very much. Thank you.
--[BOY 13B] Yeah!
--[BOY 13A] Over here!
[BOY 13A]
Come on, hurry up!
[ROXY] It's been six years
since I left Buena Village.
I wonder how much
Rudy has grown.
[clanking]
[gasps]
[ROXY] A red-headed swordsman
and a tall, bald spearman.
I wonder if they're
from "Dead End."
And if they are, where the
tiny Kennel Master might be.
[ROXY]
They're both so strong.
Don't tell me they
really are Superd.
[ROXY]
Th-Those eyes.
They wouldn't attack me just for
watching them train, would they?
[ELINALISE moans] Yes! Don't
stop, you hairy stinky beasts!
Put a baby in me!
[ELINALISE moaning]
[ELINALISE] Why, Roxy,
when did you get back?
You're welcome to
join us, if you like.
[moans]
[ELINALISE]
Who said stop, you idiot?
[ELINALISE moaning]
[gasps]
Hey! Wait!
[ROXY] Icicle Break!
Icicle Break! Icicle Break!
[ELINALISE]
Calm down, would you?
Those repairs were steep.
We'll have to watch
our spending for a while.
I wish we at least had
some intel to show for it.
I hope you realize
it's your fault we don't.
I was admirably
performing my duties
and simply happened to receive
an enticing invitation.
Well, you still didn't have to.
You know what I mean?
There were five of them!
You'll understand
one day, sweetheart.
It's not every day
that a strong,
beautiful adventurer like me
gets to melt helplessly
into the arms of
thugs like them.
Ugh, just thinking about it
is almost enough
to get me pregnant.
[ROXY]
I don't need to know that.
[ELINALISE] Oh, you'll lighten
up after you've had your first.
I can help you find him!
Why not join me next time--
That's never going to happen.
[TALHAND sighs]
I know how I'll find him:
in the dark depths of
a dangerous labyrinth.
When all hope seems lost,
he'll come to my rescue.
A tall and slender young man
with boyish charm.
We'll combine our strength
to fight our way out,
and that's when our love
will bud and blossom,
and then, by the time
we manage to escape...
[ELINALISE chuckles]
Goodness, you're such a child.
Ahem! Forget I said anything!
Let's just focus on
getting to the next town!
[ELINALISE]
Yes, ma'am.
[RUDEUS]
Gallus' terms were as follows:
He would smuggle
Ruijerd to Zant Port
if we agreed to liberate
some "stolen goods"
for him upon arrival.
He's kind of a sketchy guy,
but I didn't have many options.
[RUDEUS] If I know dating sims,
and I think I do,
a sea voyage is the perfect
place for a major event!
An octopus, squid,
sea serpent, pirates?
Maybe a ghost ship?
Something like that will
sink us and set us adrift.
Then the love interest
and I wash up
on a desert island and
start a new life together.
At first, she won't
be able to stand me,
but as the days draw on,
her heart will soften,
and soon she'll fall for me.
And once that happens, well,
you know what happens next.
[RUDEUS]
Our eyes meet.
Our passion kindles.
Our hearts pound!
Our sweat flies!
The surf roars!
I make a cup of coffee.
And we live happily ever after.
[BOTH laughing]
[RUDEUS]
Unfortunately, reality is cruel.
[ERIS retches]
Rudeus. Am I gonna die?
You can be honest.
[RUDEUS]
If you die of seasickness,
I will make fun of you.
Sorry, I'll be back in a sec.
I gotta go hit the head.
[ERIS]
'Kay, good luck.
[RUDEUS sighs]
You smell funny now.
[ERIS]
I'm so glad we made it.
I'm never gonna
get on a boat again.
You say that,
but we'll have to take one
from here to the Central
Continent eventually,
so get ready.
[ERIS] No. Will you cast Healing
on me the whole way again?
[RUDEUS]
If you want, but I might hafta
do somethin' naughty to you.
[ERIS groans]
Please don't tease me like that.
[RUDEUS] I am not teasing!
I'm controlling myself!
[RUDEUS] Hey, it's all I can do
to keep myself in check.
[ERIS]
Well, that's fine, I guess.
You can touch me
a little bit next time
if you really want to.
[RUDEUS] Yeah, no, sorry,
"a little" isn't gonna cut it.
Let's just wait until you're
ready to get real messed up.
Anyway.
It's about time
to go pick up Ruijerd.
Are you good to
hold down the fort?
[ERIS]
Yup. You got it.
[RUDEUS] Don't give me
a chance to cave, Eris.
Let me keep my promise!
[RUDEUS yells]
[SMUGGLER 13A]
He wouldn't quit wailin', so I
wound up having to
off the bastard.
[SMUGGLER 13B laughs]
Pay up, chump!
[SMUGGLER 13C]
Go easy on me next time, man.
[RUDEUS]
What an elaborate hideout.
I guess that's career
criminals for you.
[RUDEUS]
That dog is huge.
[SMUGGLER 13D]
What're you starin' at?
Sorry, forgot my manners.
[PRISONER 13A cries]
[SMUGGLER 13E] Enough already,
you annoying little shit.
--[thud]
--[PRISONER 13A groans]
[PRISONER 13A crying]
[SMUGGLER 13E]
Ugh, dammit.
[thudding]
[SMUGGLER 13F]
Here you go.
[RUDEUS] You did great, Ruijerd.
Thanks for being so patient.
[RUIJERD]
Rudeus, listen close.
There are captive children here.
Five of them.
There were six, but they killed
one for crying too loudly.
Are they the "goods"
we're liberating?
Who else do they
have chained up?
[RUIJERD]
It's just them.
I haven't sensed
any other prisoners.
I assume we'll
save them immediately?
Of course.
But all these guards
are gonna pose a problem.
What do we do?
[RUIJERD]
We kill them.
[RUDEUS]
All of them?
[RUIJERD]
They beat and murder children.
[SMUGGLER 13F]
What're you two yappin' about?
Take yer freak
and roll out already.
[RUDEUS]
Come on, think.
I'd prefer to
settle this peacefully.
But with security like this,
there's no way
we'll avoid a fight.
Problem is,
he can't kill anyone,
he has the Superd's
reputation to rebuild.
So I have to do it.
And really, what's stopping me?
They killed someone first!
Yeah, an eye for an eye.
[RUIJERD]
Rudeus.
[gasps]
[RUIJERD] Relax. You don't
have to get your hands dirty.
[gasps] No, we're
in this together.
[RUIJERD] Those hands
are for protecting Eris.
Let me handle this. Okay?
I'm so sorry.
[SMUGGLER 13F]
Whoa. Hey, now.
Ha! Look at that.
Don't know why, but I didn't
expect you to be a real Superd.
[RUDEUS]
It's okay, I'm here to help.
[MINITONA growls]
Whoa, hey, please
don't get upset,
I'm trying to get
you out of here--
See, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm gonna save you.
[ALL gasp]
Huh? Everything okay?
It's just me.
Don't worry. It's over.
Nice timing, I just finished
healing their injuries.
[RUDEUS] Although, I can't
help the one who died.
[MINITONA growls]
[RUIJERD]
I'm sorry I couldn't save you.
These kids are all
beast people, right?
[RUIJERD] Yes. Those fiends
must have kidnapped them
from the surrounding tribes.
Disgraceful.
[ALL gasp]
[RUDEUS]
"Meow"? She meowed!
Not like Eris's
fake-ass imitation,
a real, genuine "meow"!
[RUDEUS]
Will you get them back to town
while I look for the dog?
Naturally. Tread carefully,
and we'll see you there.
[RUDEUS]
Sounds good.
[whimpers]
There you are.
[RUDEUS]
Let's get you outta here, huh?
That felt good. Barrier magic?
[RUDEUS]
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
Huh.
[RUDEUS]
Okay. That was easy.
Huh?
[RUDEUS laughs]
Oh, stop, puppy!
I have a wife and
a husband and a family--
Oh, what?
[RUDEUS]
He's so frickin' fluffy!
[RUDEUS squeals] Oh, this is
the best day of my life!
[gasps] Careful, boy!
[roars]
[RUDEUS]
Huh? Oh, no. That's not good.
What did he do to me?
[RUDEUS]
I can't move!
[RUDEUS] No, I was born with
a lewd expression on my face!
There's a difference!
Let me defend myself!
[RUDEUS]
Excuse you!
[barks]
[RUDEUS] Nope! Wait!
Hold it, hang on a second!
I'm innocent,
I tell you! Innocent!