[RUDEUS]
Hello there.
I'm Rudeus,
a former jobless bum.
Today, we're looking
at a hot new apartment
that can be yours for
the low, low price of free!
No deposit, no fees, no rent!
It's a homey,
shabby-chic number
made from hardy,
locally sourced wood.
For your convenience,
it comes furnished
with a rustic straw bed.
Mind the bugs, heh!
There's an en suite
bathroom as well,
you just do your
business in this hole!
As a modern boy, I'm a little
iffy on how hygienic that is.
But you just can't
beat this price!
Nothing's cheaper than free!
And lest I forget, breakfast
and dinner are included!
The food here is
nothing to sneeze at.
I don't know what kind
of meat this is,
but for anyone who's used to
life on the Demon Continent,
its tenderness and flavor
are like no other.
[RUDEUS] Now for this
apartment's greatest feature:
its reassuring security.
Check out these sturdy beams!
I couldn't budge them
if I wanted!
Believe you me,
one look at these
would make any
burglar think twice.
And yet, criminals
still manage to
find their way
inside constantly.
'Cause after all,
this is a prison.
[RUDEUS]
So. Now what am I gonna do?
[RUDEUS] It'd be easy enough
to open the lock with magic,
but I'm in the middle
of a forest.
Getting lost in a place like
this would not end well.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS] Guess stripping me
naked wasn't enough.
They have to douse me
in cold water
and insult me on top of it!
What'll I do if this
gives me a new fetish?
O Goddess,
grant me your protection!
[RUDEUS sneezes]
[birds squawking]
[RUDEUS]
I shouldn't do anything rash.
I'll wait for Ruijerd and
Eris to save the day.
[RUDEUS]
Although, I wouldn't have to
if these people would
just listen to me.
[RUDEUS] Put those big ears
to use, why don't ya?
[RUDEUS]
Ruijerd's taking his sweet time.
What's the deal?
I wonder if he got into
it with that older warrior
who ran off after him
and the kids.
Or if maybe something
happened to Eris?
No, they can handle themselves.
No point in catastrophizing.
Besides, it's only day three.
"Good things come
to those who wait."
This sucks.
[GEESE gasps]
Hey, that hurt!
Don't ignore me!
Would it kill ya
to be a little gentler?
[groans]
[GEESE gasps]
Welcome, traveler.
I'm afraid you've reached
the end of the line.
What's wrong? Flustered?
[GEESE] No, you just
struck me as, um, cocky.
Watch it, new guy,
I've been in here
longer than you,
which means I'm
the master of this cell!
Show some respect!
[GEESE]
Uh, 'kay.
Good, now please,
make yourself comfortable.
Let's chat:
what's a guy like you
doing in a place like this?
Oh. Their guards
caught me cheating, is all.
[RUDEUS]
Ooh, a gambling man!
Was it rock-paper-scissors?
Crossing steel beams?
No, what the hell are those?
It was dice.
What about you, boss?
I hugged a silver dog
and the next thing I knew,
I was rotting in prison.
[GEESE]
Oh, that was you?
Everyone's been talking about
how the Doldias' Sacred Beast
got attacked by
a "beast" in heat.
[RUDEUS]
These folks got jokes, huh?
So what's your name, new guy?
It's Geese.
[RUDEUS]
Cool. I'm Rudeus.
Huh? Rudeus. I swear I've
heard that name before.
I'm sure a lot of people
have this name.
[GEESE]
Yeah, you're prob'ly right.
Oh. Sorry to change
the subject, but I gotta ask.
Before you were arrested,
did you happen to see
a redheaded girl
or a tall bald guy
out there looking for me?
Nope, Not that I recall.
Why, do you owe 'em
money or something--?
No! I was imprisoned here
on false charges!
But neither of my companions
have shown up to rescue me!
Ah! Yeah, that's gotta suck.
I-I'm sorry to hear that.
[RUDEUS]
Hey, don't give me that tone!
It's not like they up and
ditched me or anything!
They're probably just
taking extra care
to find the kids' parents.
Yeah. That's gotta be it.
[RUDEUS]
Ahh, right there.
You're pretty good
at this, new guy.
[GEESE chuckles]
I can do just about anything.
[RUDEUS]
Oh yeah?
Can you take down
a full-grown dragon
with your bare hands?
[GEESE] Well no,
nothing quite like that.
I'm not much of a fighter.
A pacifist?
Then, can you satisfy
a hundred women at once?
[GEESE] Ha, one is enough
for me. Two, tops.
[RUDEUS] Hmm. Well, can you
tell me how to get back
to Zant Port from here?
[GEESE gasps]
How come? Gonna make
a break for it?
[RUDEUS] I'm getting worried
about my friends.
[GEESE] Look. If you wanna run,
you're on your own!
Really? You could at least
guide me part of the way!
Hey, all I want is to
serve my time, man!
If you really are innocent,
why don't you just tell them?
Do you honestly think
I haven't tried that already?
No one will listen
to a word I say!
Fine! I'll take
the guard hostage
and make her
lead me back to town!
Wait! Calm down!
Get your hands off me, newbie,
I've had it with this place!
I'll burn this forest to
the ground if I have to!
Huh? Uh, not seeing the guard.
Is it just me,
or is it hot in here?
Yeah, now that you mention it,
I guess it is
getting a little warm.
And kinda-sorta smoky?
That, uh, wasn't you, right?
[GEESE]
Then that means...
[BOTH]
Wildfire!
We'll get roasted
alive if we don't
think fast, boss! What do we do?
Duh! We bust outta here, genius!
How do we do that with no key?
Like this, of course!
I got it, let's roll.
Didn't even break a sweat!
That's why you're the boss!
[GEESE]
This is horrible.
I heard someone
had been kidnapping
and selling beast kids lately.
I wonder if these
are the same guys.
[RUDEUS] Whatever they want,
they're going way too far.
After almost a week
of languishing
in a cell on trumped-up charges,
I've been feeling
a little vindictive
towards these villagers.
So I wouldn't mind seeing them
get their just desserts.
[RUDEUS]
But this? This is too much.
It's nauseating.
Are you gonna get going or what?
'Cause I don't think you could
ask for a better distraction.
[RUDEUS]
They're gonna owe me.
[gasps] For what, boss?
For saving every last
one of their hides!
[gasps] All right,
I like your style!
Leave the front line to me!
[GEESE]
Take this! Yeesh, that hurt!
We're all clear!
[RUDEUS] I need all the
cold air I can manage!
[GEESE]
That's insane!
[grunts]
Wow, you made that look easy!
[SMUGGLER 14G] They've got
a mage! Kill 'im!
I won't let you guys
lay a finger on the boss!
[RUDEUS] This is bad.
Should I retreat?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps] It's you!
We'll talk later!
Your pathetic crew
is no match for me
now that I can smell again.
[RUDEUS]
Whoa. He's cool.
[GYES] I'm taking our children
back. Will you help me?
Yes, sir!
Quit yer cryin' and pile in!
Is everyone all right up there?
[GYES]
Of course they're not all right.
[GALLUS]
Ah, come on.
[GALLUS] They're all
still breathin', aren't they?
It figures you were behind this.
Who else?
But I'm surprised you've
turned coat, Kennel Master.
Especially considering
your companions
have done a mighty fine job
keeping the Doldia warriors
occupied for us.
I wondered what was
taking them so long.
How did we let this happen?
[GEESE]
Hang on, you know this guy?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah. Sorta.
Lest we all forget where
your loyalties oughtta lie.
Without me,
you'd still be stranded
on that hellscape
Demon Continent.
[RUDEUS] So this was your
plan from the beginning.
[GALLUS]
Now you're gettin' it!
We took the kids
in the first place,
we only wanted
you to set them free
to draw the warriors'
attention away from here
and out to the docks.
Then your Superd buddy
could kill 'em
and we could charge the village
and take the rest of the kids.
How elaborate. Rude, though.
I thought you were supposed to
cut your partners in
on this kind of thing.
[GALLUS] Well if that's all
you want, be my guest!
These Doldia brats fetch an
exceptionally
high price, you know.
Some pervy noble family in the
Asura Kingdom loves 'em. Ha, ha!
Those freaks will pay
anything we ask!
[RUDEUS]
It couldn't be. Yes it could.
Think I'm gonna pass.
[GALLUS] Heh. Is Dead End
trying to play the hero?
Yeah, I'd like it
to look that way.
I see. Well, friend,
you've chosen poorly!
[gasps]
[GALLUS grunts]
[RUDEUS gasps]
[GEESE] You're gonna
want to watch yourself
around this guy, boss.
That's North God Style!
Hey, you know
your stuff, monkey man!
And I'm Saint-class to boot.
Hence, Gallus "the Cleaner."
So are we going to have it out,
or are you suddenly
getting cold feet?
Surely you're not so spineless
as to let me get
away unchallenged.
[RUDEUS]
"You rat bastard!
How dare you
take a child hostage!"
That's what I'd like to say.
But this guy's strong.
[RUDEUS]
Maybe I should let him go.
Unlike Ruijerd,
I'm not righteous enough
to risk my own life
for a bunch of kids
I don't even know.
Wow, you are gonna back off!
Boring, but I get it.
And this does us both a favor.
Drop me a line if you ever
wanna team up again.
[RUDEUS gasps]
You can't seriously
be okay with this!
[BEAST CHILD 14D crying]
[barks]
[RUDEUS gasps]
What the hell?
[RUDEUS grunts]
I gotcha!
You asshole!
You just crossed a line!
Now that's more like it, boss!
You wouldn't let us
die that easy!
[RUDEUS]
Well, I'm in this deep.
I might as well
see this through.
[LEO barks]
Sorry, Gallus.
I changed my mind.
'Cause, like I said,
"Dead End"
will not be a villain.
You're a real pain
in the ass, kid.
[GALLUS yells]
[LEO barks]
Too easy!
[RUDEUS]
I can see him! I can win!
[GALLUS yells]
[gasps]
[GALLUS]
Ha! It's over, Kennel Master!
[gasps]
Stay out of my way!
Eat sand, jerk!
[yells]
[screams]
Did we get him?
[GEESE]
Hey, we did!
Way to go, boss!
Boss? Boss!
[LEO panting]
[ERIS]
Rudeus!
[RUDEUS]
Eris. Where are we?
[RUIJERD]
The Dedoldia chieftain's house.
[ERIS]
Tell me everything!
I heard you that fought
a North Saint and won!
That monkey-faced guy
has practically
been over the moon about it!
I beat him?
That's good. I suppose.
[GYES]
Please forgive me!
I didn't realize
that you were the one
who rescued our young ones
from those miserable fiends!
Thus, I am prepared to accept
whatever punishment you see fit!
Young Master Rudeus, as
chieftain of the Dedoldia tribe,
I, too, wish to
reiterate my gratitude.
I thank you.
Hey, Eris.
The longer I waited, the more I
worried about you and Ruijerd.
Did something go wrong?
[ERIS]
Oh, yeah! It was awful!
Lie down!
I'll tell you all about it!
[RUDEUS] Eris was overjoyed
to regale me with tales about
what happened to them during
my far less exciting
week in prison.
Once the chieftain,
Gustav, and the rest of
the Doldia warriors
caught up with Ruijerd,
there was yet another
misunderstanding
that nearly led to
some serious bloodshed.
[RUDEUS]
Not that I'm surprised.
Ruijerd doesn't exactly
have a silver tongue.
Once that was cleared up,
though, they defeated--
by which I mean slaughtered--
what was left of
the smugglers' ring.
And yet, officials in Zant Port
nearly pinned their crimes
on Ruijerd and the Doldias.
Sounds like a pretty bad week.
Eris actually chose to
stay out of the whole thing.
She took it upon herself
to guard the kids,
grinning from ear to ear
the whole time.
Maybe that's her
Greyrat blood at work.
[chuckles] I guess
it is cool that we're
in a village of
nothing but beastfolk!
This'll make a great story
for the Boreas family
when we get back!
Won't it? My grandfather
is gonna be super jealous.
Oh, I can't wait to see him!
[GRABEL] Sauros Boreas Greyrat,
overlord of Fittoa.
The negligence and
gross incompetence
you have exhibited in
response to this mana disaster
have thrown our people
into nigh irreparable chaos.
You are hereby
relieved of your duty
and sentenced to
death by beheading.
[DARIUS] Rest easy knowing
your dear Fittoa will be safe
in the hands of your
humble servant Darius.
[SAUROS]
Lowlife scum.
Eris. My dearest granddaughter.
If you still draw breath...
[SAUROS] ...I wish you
a lifetime of happiness.