Huh?
[RUDEUS]
Well. Guess it's over.
[sighs]
Hey, nice to meet you!
Rudeus, right?
Excuse me, but who
or what are you?
You mean you can't tell?
[RUDEUS]
You're just kinda blurry.
I'm a god!
The Man‐God, specifically.
"Man‐God." If you say so.
[MAN‐GOD] And you're leading
quite an interesting life.
I've been watching you
for some time.
So you're a voyeur.
Yes, you could say that,
and I've enjoyed the show.
But I decided it was
time to intervene.
Don't worry, I'm on your side.
Ha! "My side"? Now that's rich!
Why would you even
get my hopes up?
I thought I was reborn, but no.
So I hope you enjoyed
yourself, sadist.
I have no reason
to trust you now!
Somebody's touchy.
Well. I have a little
friendly advice.
Yeah, you and every
other jerk I've ever known.
Take your self‐help
crap and shove it.
That's not what I‐‐
You can't possibly
think an attitude change
is gonna make a difference.
Being optimistic
only sets you up
for way more pain down the line.
Like right now!
[MAN‐GOD]
You've misunderstood me.
I want to help you,
not the past you.
Then why do I look like this?
[MAN‐GOD]
It's your astral form.
Your body's the same.
So you mean...
This is the dream,
and I'm not actually
stuck back in this shitty body?
Yes!
When you wake up, you'll be
exactly as you left yourself.
Okay then. That's a relief.
I imagine! I was surprised!
Your mental image
of yourself is,
let's say "different,"
sugar bear.
So? What do you want with me?
You gonna send me
back to my world
'cause I don't belong here, or?
[MAN‐GOD]
Oh, of course not.
I couldn't send you
anywhere outside
the Six‐Sided World
even if I wanted to.
[sighs] If you can't
send me back,
then you must not be the one
who reincarnated me here.
No, sir. Reincarnation would be
the wicked
Dragon‐God's department.
[RUDEUS]
Great, evil dragon.
So, advice, how 'bout it?
[RUDEUS]
Nope.
Uh‐‐ And why not?
You're shady.
[MAN‐GOD]
Aw, come on!
Don't be stubborn,
just give me a chance!
No thanks, I'm not
gonna fall for
the "just the tip" approach.
You kinda suck as a conman.
[MAN‐GOD]
Ugh, you wound me.
But ignore me if you want.
It's your funeral.
My what? What do you mean?
Well, the Demon Continent
is a harsh land.
There's barely any food,
and it's crawling with monsters.
Think you can handle it?
[RUDEUS] Wha? Why would
I be way out there?
You, my friend,
were caught up in
a huge mana disaster
and got teleported.
[RUDEUS] I guess now I know what
that explosion of light was.
So what do you think, boo boo?
Are you confident
you can survive,
stranded in a dangerous land?
[RUDEUS]
Fine! I get your point.
Go ahead, give me
whatever advice you want.
[MAN‐GOD]
Good, good. Now. Rudeus.
Listen closely.
When you wake up,
there will be a man nearby.
Rely on that man, okay?
And. Help him.
Whatever it takes.
[RUDEUS gasps]
[RUDEUS pants]
That's a relief.
Where's Ghislaine?
Is that you?
[gasps] A Superd!
Huh?
[RUDEUS]
Um, hello.
I don't understand
your question.
I watched you two
fall from the sky.
I know human children are frail,
so I made a fire to warm you.
[RUDEUS]
Uh. You saved us, then.
Thank you for that.
[RUDEUS] There wasn't, um,
anyone else nearby, was there?
A beast‐woman?
[RUIJERD] I only found
the two of you. My apologies.
No, that's all right.
Does the sight of me
not frighten you, boy?
It would be rude to be afraid
of you after you rescued us.
Interesting. You are
a very strange child.
[ERIS grunts]
[RUDEUS]
I'm Rudeus Greyrat, by the way.
Ruijerd Superdia.
[RUDEUS]
Pardon. May I sit?
So. Where are we?
The Northeast Demon Continent.
The Biegoya region.
[RUDEUS]
Hard to believe.
We're a long way from home.
[RUDEUS] Getting back
to the Central Continent
won't exactly be
a walk in the park.
[RUIJERD] How did you
come to be here, child?
Not sure.
I think we got caught up in some
kind of giant mana disaster.
[RUIJERD]
Fear not.
It will be my pleasure
to protect you from harm.
[RUDEUS]
Huh?
I swear on the honor
of the Superd.
You will see
your homeland again.
For whatever that's worth,
I'm sure you know
our reputation.
[ERIS gasps, screams]
Eris! Good,
you're awake. This is...
No. You're...
You're a... Superd!
Somebody help me! No!
I don't want to die!
Where's Ghislaine?
I want Ghislaine!
Please come back,
I don't wanna die!
I'm sorry, Rudeus, I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry I pushed you away!
Now I'll never get to keep
my promise to you! And I...
[cries]
[RUIJERD]
That's a normal reaction.
[RUDEUS]
So I'm the weird one?
[RUIJERD]
You are. But...
In a good way.
[ERIS]
It's n‐nice...
Nice to make your acquaintance.
I'm Eris Bo‐Bo‐Boreas Greyrat.
How do you do, sir?
Your name's Eris
Boboboreas Greyrat?
[ERIS]
No! It's "Boreas"!
I just stuttered a little!
[RUIJERD grunts]
Forgive me.
I'm Ruijerd, uh, Superdia.
[RUDEUS]
See? He's not so bad!
You just gotta communicate.
Huh?
Honestly, my mother
is such a liar!
She said a Superd would eat me
if I stayed up too late!
[RUDEUS] Oh, is that why
you hid under a blanket?
Don't make fun of me!
Ruijerd's kind of a loner,
so I bet he'd be
your friend if you asked.
I dunno.
[RUDEUS] Isn't that right?
What do you say?
Uh. Of course.
If you like. I'd appreciate it.
Well. Yes! If you insist!
I suppose I can be your friend!
[RUDEUS] That was all
it took to break through
the last of her defenses.
She's back to the Eris
we know and love,
but even when she's rude,
he just brushes it off.
Whoever said the Superd
have short tempers
was clearly full of it.
We'll get our
bearings tomorrow.
But I know we have
a tough road ahead of us.
[RUDEUS] I have to get her home
if it's the last thing I do.
Look at all that!
Let's get to adventuring!
[RUIJERD] I thought I
told you to stay put.
How come you always know exactly
where the monsters will be?
[RUIJERD] I can see them
with the eye in my forehead.
That's handy!
[RUIJERD] I've wished many times
that I didn't have it at all.
[ERIS] Well, I'll take it
if you don't want it!
Lemme yank it out!
[RUIJERD]
I can't do that.
[RUDEUS]
I hope she's joking.
If I had a sword, I could
totally help you fight!
And I'm sure the magic
I know could be pretty useful.
[RUIJERD] Don't concern
yourselves with combat.
I want you and your big brother
to stay out of harm's way.
[ERIS]
Excuse me?
I'm way older than
he is, you got that?
[RUIJERD]
Oh, uh. Apologies.
[RUDEUS]
Oof. Poor Ruijerd.
[gasps]
[RUIJERD]
There it is.
[ERIS]
A village!
Rudeus! What's going
on over there?
He doesn't want to let us in
because you and I
are too suspicious.
He'll fetch an authority.
The chief is sure to let you in.
[RUDEUS sighs]
Telepathy.
The Migurd tribe can speak
with each other at a distance.
Did you say Migurd?
[RUDEUS] Hell yeah,
Demon‐God paying off!
My name is Rokkus,
I'm the elder.
But wait. However
did you come by
that pendant you're
wearing, young man?
[RUDEUS]
And of course he speaks Human.
My master gave this to me.
Really? And who was that?
Oh, her name is Roxy!
Eh?
[RUDEUS]
Is this her freakin' hometown?
[gasps] Rudeus! Come look at the
weird thing guarding the fields!
That's so cool!
Their houses are
giant tortoise shells!
[RUDEUS]
One Roxy.
Two Roxys.
Three Roxys.
My goddess. This is heaven.
[RUDEUS gasps]
Twenty years?
[RUDEUS]
M‐‐Mm‐hmm.
That's a good dad.
[RUDEUS] I kinda wonder
if Paul and the others
are that worried about us.
[ROKKUS]
A mana disaster.
I suppose that accounts
for the shooting stars
flying every which
way last night.
I wondered what had gone awry.
[RUDEUS]
Thank you for sheltering us.
[ROKKUS] Hmm. What could
have triggered that?
[ROKKUS]
My, aren't you two close?
Yeah, we are.
So, tell me.
How do you intend to
make your way back home?
I'm going to escort them.
I refuse to leave them alone.
Have you thought that through?
You're only so useful.
What do you mean by that?
I can navigate and fight.
I'm more than capable
of protecting them.
In the wild.
But you can't enter cities.
Huh? Wait a sec, is that true?
If they needed help,
I'd force my way in.
Even if I had to kill
everyone inside to find them.
As expected.
There's simply no reasoning with
you when children are involved.
What has it been, ten years now?
Since you saved one
of our little ones?
I know your goal
is important to you,
but surely you
won't accomplish it
through such violent means.
[RUDEUS]
Umm.
If you don't mind,
what goal is that?
To restore his tribe's honor.
He wants to convince everyone
that the Superd aren't
the iniquitous monsters
they're made out to be.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
Well. Good luck.
If Roxy and Eris
are any indication,
fear of the Superd
is deeply ingrained
in this world's culture.
How can one guy expect
to change that on his own?
[RUDEUS] I see how rumors
can get out of hand,
but it's true that
the Superd turned on
their allies
during the war, right?
[RUIJERD]
We did not! That's a lie.
We were victims
of the devil Laplace.
So. What happened?
He repaid our loyalty
with betrayal.
Do you mind telling me more?
[RUDEUS] So he did.
And the story he told
revealed a hidden, tragic side
of this world's history.
[RUDEUS]
A new weapon?
[RUIJERD] Yes. Before invading
the Central Continent,
he presented us with new spears.
Many of my warriors
objected at first.
We had our own,
and a Superd's spear
is their very soul,
so why abandon it?
[RUDEUS] Four hundred years ago,
the hero Laplace fought
to unify demonkind
and win rights
the humans had long denied them.
The Superd were some of
his earliest supporters.
So eventually, Ruijerd
and his men accepted
the spears they were awarded.
[RUIJERD]
They were incredibly powerful.
We were nearly
invincible in battle.
But they were corrupting us.
[RUIJERD] Before we knew it,
we lost the ability
to distinguish friend from foe.
And we showed no mercy.
Somehow, we couldn't recognize
the change in each other.
The mere thought of
bloodshed brought us joy.
Soon enough...
If anyone crossed our path,
they were cut down.
And then we were lured home.
There were no survivors.
Parents, spouses,
siblings, children.
In our madness,
we slaughtered our own families.
So here we are.
This spear is all
that's left of my son.
He sacrificed himself
to save me from that curse.
Our infamy is our punishment
for foolishly trusting a devil.
It's not my fault,
but all the same,
I brought shame to my tribe.
I will not rest.
As the leader of our warriors,
I want to tell our story
and clear our names.
[RUDEUS]
Four hundred years.
Has he been alone ever since?
Driven by bitterness and misery.
Fighting with his own regret.
[RUDEUS]
I know how that goes.
I understand.
And maybe having
a human child on your side
could open up some
new possibilities.
[RUDEUS]
So if you'll let me. I promise.
I'll do whatever
it takes to help you.
[gasps]
Thank you.
You're Master's mother?
[ROKARI gasps]
[RUDEUS]
Okay.
[gasps]
Goodbye. And thank you
for your kindness!
[RUDEUS]
Here we go. Just us and Ruijerd.
[RUDEUS] The old me probably
would have laughed off
his sob story and
been done with it.
[RUDEUS] But he really struck
a chord with me last night.
And it feels safe
to trust him. So I will.
[RUDEUS]
He'll protect us on the road.
We'll protect him in the cities.
We'll rely on each other.
[RUDEUS] Ruijerd? I'm really
glad to have you with us.
[RUIJERD]
Thanks.