[ERIS]
This sword is amazing!
[RUDEUS gasps]
Eris, you know you can leave
some of them for me
to handle, right?
Sorry, what'd you say?
This is a dream come true!
I love living like this!
[RUDEUS]
Guh. I miss beef.
What's a guy gotta do
for a burger around here?
Look there.
[ERIS, RUDEUS gasp]
[RUIJERD] Beyond those cliffs
is the city of Rikarisu.
[RUDEUS]
Lizard guy? Koala guy? Whoa.
Rudeus, are you seeing this?
They're all so crazy‐lookin'!
I expected most demons
to look like humans,
like the Migurd and Superd,
but I guess that's not the case.
Yes, there are many different
tribes across the continent.
What's "Dead End"?
They all seem
pretty scared of it.
[RUIJERD]
That would be me.
Huh?
Say wha?
[RUIJERD] That's how some
refer to me these days.
[RUDEUS gasps]
[RUDEUS]
That's a little much, isn't it?
But I guess they do think
he's a mass murderer.
So what do we do now?
Go without me.
I'll leap over the cliffs
and meet you inside.
Hang on!
You can't just drop down
on their heads like that,
the whole city is gonna freak!
You got a better idea?
[RUDEUS groans]
[RUDEUS]
Yes, I do! Come here a sec.
[ERIS gasps]
Ta‐da!
It's cute on you.
[ERIS] Thanks, Rudeus!
I'll take good care of it!
Okay, we all need to
keep our eyes peeled
for the Adventurers' Guild.
Are we gonna join?
I really wanna!
Yeah, that's part of the plan,
we gotta make money
somehow, don't we?
So let's go! Today we
become adventurers!
[ERIS]
All right!
Don't fall behind, Ruijerd!
This is where it gets serious.
Yes, right.
[DEMONS chattering]
[DEMON GOAT 10A laughs]
[ALL]
Huh?
Uh...
[RUDEUS chuckles]
[DEMON DOGS laugh]
[DEMONS laugh]
[PERTOKO laughs]
[ALL laughing]
Now, for your party name.
Are you sure you want
to go with "Dead End"?
I've never been more
sure about anything.
[PERTOKO laughs]
All newly‐formed parties
start at F rank.
Remember, you can
only accept jobs
within one rank of
your own. Understand?
Yes.
[ERIS] Now I'm an adventurer
for real! Let's go, Rudeus!
I can't read this!
[RUDEUS] What's the
highest‐paying gig we can get?
The monster‐hunting jobs
start at Rank C.
We'd have to get promoted
twice first. That's a shame.
[laughs]
Why did we even register if you
weren't gonna take any jobs?
I thought we would be out there
slaying dragons already!
We'll work our way
up to dragons.
Today was successful
enough on its own.
How do you figure?
Please explain.
We introduced you as Dead End,
and everybody there laughed
instead of screaming
or running away.
That's progress.
And now the fun begins.
I know we're pretending
you're Migurdian for now,
but if "Dead End" the party
starts doing good deeds,
that ought to help "Dead End"
the Superd regain his honor.
But don't lose that, all right?
It was a gift from my master.
I expect it back.
Right.
[ERIS gasps]
[ERIS]
It's so pretty!
I've never seen anything
like it! [laughs]
I vote we find a place to sleep.
We're gonna be really busy soon.
Indeed. Let's go.
[gasps] Don't touch me!
[ERIS]
You. You'll pay for that!
This is the first
piece of clothing
that Rudeus ever
bought for me, you jerk!
Eris, that's enough!
Down girl! Heel!
[RUDEUS] Eh... Something about
this makes me feel itchy.
[RUDEUS sighs] Hey. I'll mend
that for you tomorrow.
You mean it?
[RUDEUS]
All right, next steps.
First and foremost,
we need money.
The inn is 15 stone
pieces a night,
which the low‐rank jobs
will barely cover.
With food and supplies,
we'll be broke in two weeks.
Heh. Look at me,
fretting over the family budget.
Never thought I'd see the day.
[chuckles]
[RUDEUS]
Again? What do you want now?
[MAN‐GOD]
I'm so proud!
You took my advice and Ruijerd
got you to the nearest city!
Ha. He would have
protected us anyway.
Even if we'd run.
That's just the kinda guy he is.
My goodness, it certainly
sounds like you trust him.
So, why are you still
so suspicious of me?
[RUDEUS] Really?
I thought that was obvious.
[MAN‐GOD chuckles]
Oh well.
I have some more
advice for you anyway.
[RUDEUS]
Yeah, whatever. Make it quick.
[MAN‐GOD]
Come on, lighten up a little!
[RUDEUS] I hate this place
and I hate this body.
And I hate your stupid voice,
so let's get this over with.
Ugh, well, you're no fun.
[RUDEUS] I'm already
in the palm of your hand.
Don't be silly.
You can ignore me!
What you do next
is all up to you!
[RUDEUS]
Enough, spit it out.
I hear you.
[clears throat] Rudeus.
Accept the E‐rank job
to find a lost kitten.
Soon enough,
you'll find yourself
with much less to worry about.
[RUDEUS] Finding lost kittens
can't pay that much.
What are they thinking?
[RUDEUS]
Can't sleep?
Yeah.
[ERIS]
Hey. Rudeus?
[RUDEUS]
Hm?
[ERIS] Do you think we'll
actually make it home?
We'll make it.
[ERIS] And Ghislaine and
Grandfather will be okay, right?
[RUDEUS]
Yeah. Absolutely.
[RUDEUS] Here, kitty!
Where are ya? Kitty!
Are you sure we're headed
in the right direction?
Positive. Just stay behind me.
Are you using your third eye?
[RUIJERD]
Yes. Look.
There are signs
of a struggle here.
I can't tell what
you're looking at.
[RUIJERD]
This way.
In there.
[ERIS] This whole place
stinks like a farm!
[RUDEUS]
Anybody home?
[RUIJERD] No people. But many
other living creatures.
[RUDEUS] Sounds like we'd
better be careful, then.
What is this creepy place?
Found it.
[RUDEUS]
Huh? That's no kitten.
I guess everything's bigger
on the Demon Continent.
[RUDEUS] Do you think
all of them are pets?
Someone's coming.
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[RUDEUS sighs] A sneak attack
always does the trick.
But we totally just fought
like a real team, didn't we?
Yeah, we did.
[RUDEUS]
Okay, uh...
Damn. Someone teach this idiot
not to assault his captors.
He doesn't want
to make us angry.
[BOTH screaming]
Ruijerd. Why did you...?
[RUIJERD] Hm? Because he
injured a child, of course.
You. You shouldn't kill.
Why not? He hurt you.
That's no excuse.
How can you just‐‐?
[RUDEUS] Listen. You can't
do that anymore, okay?
[RUIJERD]
Why?
I... If you walk around
executing people,
it'll make the Superd's
reputation worse!
Even if they're evil?
[RUDEUS] People won't care
who you killed!
Just that you killed them!
That sounds foolish.
[gasps]
What's with you?
Stop arguing with
our party leader!
[RUIJERD] He's still
too young to understand
that I did the right thing.
That kind of attitude is
why people don't like you!
[RUDEUS] Please. Don't kill
anyone from here on out.
Prove that the Superd
aren't monsters.
Okay? Eris and I don't want
to be afraid of you, either.
I get it now.
[RUIJERD]
I told you. Villains.
[RUDEUS]
Wha‐‐ Hey, cool your jets!
Now what? Think. Think.
I thought so.
You want to join forces?
You can't be serious.
I know what I'm doing.
Would you please
be quiet for a moment?
[RUIJERD]
What?
Working together, we can
earn more money, faster.
And they can help us
improve your reputation.
Don't be absurd!
I refuse to depend on
lowlifes such as these!
[ERIS]
Let go of him!
What's your problem?
[RUIJERD]
I don't like villains.
[ERIS] Oh, boo‐hoo,
quit complaining!
Who cares if you don't like it,
he's doing all of
this for our sake!
[RUIJURD]
Huh?
What's so "villainous" about
kidnapping a few stupid animals?
They also kicked a child.
So what? I kick people
all the time!
Evildoers can't be trusted.
Yeah, well you've done some
pretty evil stuff,
too, haven't you?
[RUIJERD gasps]
[ERIS]
Rudeus is really smart, okay?
He's going to make sure
everything works out fine!
So just shut up
and do what he says!
If you don't like it,
then leave,
we can make it home without you!
[RUDEUS]
Eris. That's enough, please.
[RUIJERD]
I'm a Superd warrior.
I have never once
gone back on my word.
I will see you home
safely no matter what.
[RUDEUS]
I know.
Ooh, how much is it?
[NOKOPARA laughs]