Crazy. It's come in already?
Guess I'm growing up
faster than I thought.
Works for me.
[RUDEUS] I didn't like studying
other languages in my old life,
but these are surprisingly fun.
Whoa.
[RUDEUS] Eris has gone from
Intermediate to Advanced
in the Sword God style
in two short years.
I'm no match for her anymore.
[RUDEUS] That thing get bigger?
Seriously, what is that?
It's weirding me out.
[ERIS] Move it! Rudeus will
see us if we don't hurry!
Huh?
[ERIS]
I can't wait to see his face!
I bet he's gonna cry!
I don't know,
Master Rudeus isn't
one to wear his
heart on his sleeve.
But you do think
he'll like it, right?
Yes, of course he will.
He's suffered
so much nuisance...
[RUDEUS]
"Suffered"?
I've been pretty confident
about my work here.
But if people are talking
about me behind my back,
I'm more confident that I'll cry
myself to sleep every night.
Then we have to
give him the best
tenth birthday party we can!
[gasps]
[ERIS]
But I still wish he'd been
born into a different family.
[RUDEUS] I recently learned
why the Boreas family
can't be too public about me.
Hello, Master Rudeus,
how are you?
How do you do?
[RUDEUS] I thought it was
due to Paul's reputation,
but it's his name:
Paul Notos Greyrat.
Notos is one of the
four main Greyrat houses.
When Paul left,
his brother became
the head of that branch instead.
He's kind of a scumbag himself,
so there's a covert
movement to replace him.
Even if I'm not
the one to do that,
a member of the Notos bloodline
under the Boreas roof
could invite some unfortunate
misunderstandings.
So, I can't have a massive
shindig like Eris.
Still, they're going
out of their way
to throw me a small,
private party.
I don't care if
I have one at all,
but Eris would be disappointed
if I'm indifferent about it.
I should practice crying on cue.
[RUDEUS]
That aside.
I can't believe I've been
in this world ten years.
Everyone seems anxious today.
I can't say I've noticed.
Hey, tell me how a kid your age
learns three languages
in two years.
I've never seen
anything like that.
Well, I never would
have figured out
Beast‐God if not for you.
Studying is surprisingly
hungry work, huh?
What do you say we
go grab a snack?
[gasps]
We shouldn't do that
right before dinner.
Wh‐Why don't we just
relax in here instead?
[RUDEUS] Ah‐ha. Today's
the day, isn't it?
Yeah, we can do that.
In fact, this is
the perfect opportunity
to show you something
I've been working on.
You made a statue of me?
You've gotten
really good at these.
Oh. It's missing
my tail, though.
I don't quite understand
how they work.
[RUDEUS chuckles]
This'll be fun.
Let's see how far
she'll go to keep me here.
But I'd love to learn!
Can I see the base of your tail?
[RUDEUS] How will you get
out of this one, Ghislaine?
Oh, well if that's all you need.
No problem at all.
[RUDEUS] Just like that?
Wow. Zero hesitation.
You win this round, lady.
Is it okay if I touch it?
Of course, go right ahead.
[RUDEUS] Whoa. Talk about toned.
How is this a real butt?
Oh my God! I want
muscle like this!
[knocking]
Excuse me,
Young Master Rudeus.
Your dinner is served.
[ALL] Rudeus! From the Boreas
House, happy tenth birthday!
[laughs]
I... What is this?
Here, Rudeus. Happy birthday.
Wow. Thank you. I had
forgotten what day it was.
[RUDEUS]
I... I'm sorry.
I‐It's just that
I didn't expect...
Ever since I got here,
I've been so worried
I wasn't welcome.
I‐I never thought you would
celebrate me like this.
To arms at once!
I declare war on
the Notos House!
I'll murder Pilemon myself
and put Rudeus in charge!
[PHILIP]
Father! Restrain yourself!
Gather the troops, you fools!
Release me! Release me!
[RUDEUS] I didn't think I was
that good of an actor.
Um. Ignoring all of
that for a moment.
You better get excited,
because I've got
a surprise for you today!
Really? What kind of surprise?
[ERIS]
Take a guess!
[RUDEUS] Hmm. Wait.
Don't tell me my family's here?
[gasps] Oh, well, um.
We wrote to invite them,
but I'm afraid the
monsters have been
acting up lately,
so they couldn't make it.
I see. That's a shame.
Hey. Listen. I'm sorry,
Rudeus. Are you okay?
[RUDEUS]
Huh? Oh, no.
This isn't the mood
I wanted. Whoa!
[HILDA] It's all right, Rudeus!
We're your family now!
[RUDEUS]
Hold up.
Didn't this woman
hate me two seconds ago?
We'll adopt‐‐ No!
Why don't you
marry Eris instead?
[gasps] Mother, no!
Oh, I'm sorry, is Rudeus not
good enough for you, darling?
Rudeus is only ten!
His age is irrelevant!
And it's time you learned
to be a proper lady!
[HILDA gasps]
What are you doing?
Unhand me this instant,
I must save that poor child!
So, what is it?
The surprise you
were talking about.
R‐Right. Ahem. Now, Alphonse!
Bring it forward!
[ALPHONSE]
For you, sir.
A staff?
I do hope you find it
to your liking, Master Rudeus.
We gathered only
the finest materials
from around the world so that
Asura Kingdom's foremost
craftsman could build a staff
befitting a Water Saint.
I present Aqua Heartia.
[RUDEUS] It's not hard to see
that this thing cost a fortune.
It's gorgeous. Even if
its name is kinda lame.
You're a great mage,
so it's weird that
you don't have a staff of
your own already! Take it!
Thank you very much.
This is such an expensive gift.
You don't need to worry
about the price!
Now, let the party begin!
Rudeus. Happy birthday.
Eris actually has two brothers,
one older and one younger.
But when they were born,
my brother in the capital
took them both.
He took them?
Boreas men are raised
by the family head.
I lost the succession dispute,
so my sons were "adopted."
That's our branch's tradition.
Hilda still refuses to
accept that, of course.
Why would she?
Her children were taken
from her against her will.
That's why she hated you.
Her sons aren't
allowed in her home,
but this outsider can parade
around like he owns the place.
You see?
[gasps]
[PHILIP] I hope you don't
hold that against her.
No, that's perfectly
understandable.
That said. If you're
willing to lend a hand,
we could seize control
of the household.
[RUDEUS laughs]
What kind of political sway
does a ten‐year‐old have?
Marry Eris and lay low for now.
I'll handle the coup.
If it helps seal the deal,
I'll throw her in your bed
with her hands tied tonight.
[RUDEUS] Hang on,
does he want to put me
in charge of the family?
That's insane.
I want no part of
this power struggle.
I'll pretend you only said all
that because you're drunk.
Is that so? If you insist.
[RUDEUS]
Well. I should turn in.
[PHILIP]
Yes. Goodnight.
[RUDEUS]
Goodnight, sir.
[BEAST MAID 08B] Goodnight,
Master Rudeus. Sleep well.
Thanks, goodnight. [gasps]
[RUDEUS]
If I had taken Philip's deal,
I could have created my own
personal beast maid harem!
No! What a wasted opportunity!
[ERIS]
W‐Welcome back.
Good evening.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
I... I was afraid
you'd get lonely,
so I decided to
sleep here for tonight.
[RUDEUS]
Philip put her up to this.
But, it is nice to
see her this way.
[gasps] Rudeus?
[RUDEUS] How can I resist
the opportunity to share
my first time with
a stuck‐up, spoiled tsundere?
S‐Stop.
[gasps]
[RUDEUS]
No, I can't touch her,
that's exactly
what Philip wants!
Maybe I can scare her off?
Now that you mention it,
I am kinda lonely.
But I might try something
dirty if you stay here.
Fine, then. You can do that.
Just a little, though.
[RUDEUS gasps]
[RUDEUS] Well, how can I
refuse that offer?
Even if I am playing into
Philip's hands, this is my life.
And what's life
without a little risk?
[RUDEUS]
You're trembling.
[ERIS]
That's just your imagination!
[RUDEUS]
Her hair is so smooth.
With as much as she trains,
it's normally messier.
She cleaned it up for me.
You're really cute, Eris.
Huh? Where did that come from?
[RUDEUS]
I'm gonna touch you now.
[RUDEUS] Does that mean she's
giving me the green light?
She is, right?
That was a yes?
I'm good to go?
Well, okay! Let's do this!
[gasps] No!
I said "just a little"!
[RUDEUS]
Careful‐‐!
Rudeus! You idiot!
What the hell is wrong with me?
[RUDEUS]
I completely forgot myself.
What was I thinking?
"I know what girls want.
I've played dating sims."
This is why you died a virgin.
[RUDEUS] Everything Eris
did today was for me.
She worked so hard because
she cares about my feelings.
And I just ignored hers.
[sighs] I'm the worst.
[gasps] I'm so sorry!
Look. Today's a special day,
so I'll make an exception
and forgive you this time!
[RUDEUS]
No. Is she for real?
But, uh. It's still
too soon for that, so...
Five years! In five years,
we'll both be proper
grown‐ups, and then...
Maybe we can.
So, until then,
control yourself!
[RUDEUS gasps]
Yes, ma'am.
Good. Well, then I'm
gonna go back to bed now.
Goodnight. Sweet dreams
and whatever.
And I'll see you
tomorrow for practice!
[RUDEUS sighs]
Thank God.
[RUDEUS]
Thank God it's my birthday.
Thank God today was special.
Thank God I didn't
do anything worse. And...
[RUDEUS]
Aw, yeah!
[RUDEUS] It's settled!
She promised! To me!
Okay. No more
indulgences till then.
Five years. I'll be 15.
It feels like forever,
but... I can wait!
After all, a charged attack is
stronger the longer it's held.
Wait, five years?
[gasps] Wait! Sylphie!
[PAUL] Damn, I thought for sure
we'd found the last of them.
Where are they coming from?
Apparently the increase
in monster activity
isn't unique to our village.
I've heard reports of
the same coming in
from across the entire region.
These bastards are keeping me
from my son's tenth birthday.
Sorry, Rudeus.
Hope you can forgive me.
Hi, Zenith!
Well, good afternoon, Sylphie!
Come on, love, don't be shy!
Hey there, Norn. How are ya?
[SYLPHIE, ZENITH giggle]
[LILIA] Aisha. Make sure
you wipe the corners, too.
Okay!
Hi, Miss Lilia.
Sylphie, dear! Hello!
[SYLPHIE]
Will you send this off for me?
[LILIA]
What a cute pendant.
[SYLPHIE giggles]
I made it myself
based on one my dad's treasures.
You did a lovely job.
I'll make sure this reaches him.
It stinks that
we can't go visit,
but at least we can
still give him gifts.
Yes. I'm going to send him this.
What's in it?
Something Master Rudeus used to
keep by his side at all times.
[AISHA]
Big sis!
Aisha!
[AISHA, SYLPHIE]
Yay!
Look at you,
you're growing up so fast!
I'm so glad that Sylphie's
finally cheered up.
I couldn't believe
the way she acted out
after Master Rudeus
left for Roa.
I know! I'll need to
have a talk with Rudy
about some of the
things he taught her.
[LILIA] But her parents
said that she stopped
getting bullied shortly
thereafter. So I'm glad.
[ZENITH] Me, too. Even without
a gem in her forehead.
It's easy to mistake
her for a Superd.
What is a Superd, Mama?
You're brave for even asking!
They're the scariest demons
in the entire world.
And if you're not good,
they'll eat you for dinner!
[cries]
[ZENITH gasps] Oh, I'm sorry,
sweet girl! Don't cry!
Hey, I'm back.
You were gone a long time.
Good to see you home.
Hey, what's the matter?
Aww, c'mere, you.
Monsters again?
Uh‐huh. I don't know
what's gotten into 'em.
They're everywhere now.
[rumbling]
Storm clouds? Or what?
[PAX] Roxy, I don't care
about studying,
just take your clothes off!
Come on. For me?
[ROXY sighs]
[ROXY]
What is that?
It's directly above
Asura Kingdom.
No way. Rudeus?
[roars]
Mana pooling in the west?
What caused this madness?
No matter. I'll see for
myself soon enough.
[KISHIRIKA] Ooh, would you
look at all that juice?
Whose spell is that, We wonder?
Hey, We can't see them!
They must be shy.
What a nuisance.
[KISHIRIKA] Oh well! Guess we'll
meet them face to face!
Behold the Great Emperor
of the Demon World,
Kishirika Kishirisu!
[KISHIRIKA]
Now, soldiers! Sally forth!
[KISHIRIKA cackling]
[PERUGIUS] That light.
It resembles a summoning.
I wonder. Is someone
trying to break the seal
on the Demon God Laplace?
Hmph. Almanfi!
[ALMANFI]
Yes, sir.
[PERUGIUS] Investigate the
source of that mana cloud.
If you find the one
responsible. Kill them.
[ALMANFI]
As you wish.
[GHISLAINE] You've brought
us quite a long way.
[ERIS]
Did we come far enough for you
to show us your strongest spell?
Ta‐dah!
[RUDEUS]
Whoa. And I barely used any MP.
So. How is it?
It'll take some getting used to,
but it feels incredible.
[ERIS gasps]
Really? That's great!
[RUDEUS] Now. The moment
you've all been waiting for.
Water Saint Rudeus Greyrat's
mightiest attack!
Behold, mortals! Cumulonimbus!
[ERIS giggles]
[RUDEUS]
Gather, mana!
O, spirits of the
magnificent waters
and imperial prince
of lightning who‐‐
What the?
[ERIS] That was fast.
Is that the whole spell?
No, I'd barely gotten started.
That's concentrated mana.
How can you tell?
Should we head back to Roa?
Yes. The farther away,
the be‐‐ Get down!
What was that?
‐‐Who's he?
‐‐Start talking, now!
[ALMANFI]
I am Almanfi the Radiant.
By order of Lord Perugius,
I have come to put a stop
to this phenomenon.
[RUDEUS]
Perugius?
Rudeus, take Lady Eris
and fall back!
[ALMANFI]
Step aside, woman.
If I slay that mage,
the disturbance may cease.
I am the Sword King
Ghislaine Dedoldia.
He's under my protection,
so withdraw!
[ALMANFI]
You're a Sword King?
I swear on the
name of my master,
Sword God Gal Farion,
and the honor of Doldia.
[ALMANFI]
Hmph. If what you say is false,
Lord Perugius will
decide your fate.
No remorse for
ambushing children?
[ALMANFI] It's your own fault
for arousing suspicion here.
[RUDEUS]
Okay, calm down.
I can figure this out.
From the top.
First, the sky changed.
Then a weirdo in
a mask showed up.
Saying he was sent by a
centuries‐old legendary hero.
He attacked me because he thinks
the sky thing is my fault.
It's not, but it
sounds like he knows
more about it than we do.
Right? In which case...
[ALMANFI gasps]
Wait a second, at least
tell us what's going on‐‐
[gasps]
Lady Eris! Rudeus!
[RUDEUS]
Come on!
Eris!