[HOLMY] This is the brand-new
Spa Resort Midicians
in the suburbs of Midi City.
Today, we bring you the
behind-the-scenes footage
of when we, Criticrista,
filmed the commercial for it.
[PLANNER] So that's why
we want you, Cri-Cri,
Midi City's current top idols,
to be the beautiful
faces of our spa!
[JACKLYN]
I feel you!
So if we say it's cool,
then all the kids will wanna
hang out here too, right?
[PLANNER]
Yes, to chill out!
Hey, look at this!
They have play areas,
and hot springs where
you can soak as well.
There's so much to do here!
[PLANNER]
Yes, that's right!
And between the new restaurant
and all the poolside stands,
it looks like no one
will go hungry, either!
'Scuse me, I have a suggestion.
[PLANNER]
Yes, go ahead!
For the last line of the script,
I think it would get the
point across way better
if I said this:
"Hey, Big Brothers!
You should totally go
to Midicians Spa.
You can play, eat, and relax!"
That'll work well, yeah?
And I'll look straight
at the camera,
'cause it's real important to
make eye contact, you know.
[PLANNER]
What a wonderful idea!
[HOLMY] Today is our costume
fitting for the shoot.
Huh... There's
something missing.
What's wrong, Jacklyn?
Are you okay?
I just think it needs a little
something more to make it pop.
Ooh, maybe you're right.
Sweet, now it looks
totally savage!
[TSUKINO]
Thanks to Jacklyn's idea,
our costumes went
from "okay" to "Hey!'"
[ROSIA] Now, it's finally time
to start filming the commercial.
Today was the soft opening
of the restaurant.
And Tsukino was over the moon!
Yum!
Matcha and vanilla
swirl ice cream
is a traditional pairing that's
always super delicious;
one of my favorites.
But I didn't expect the
mix of mint and caramel
to be so amazingly yummy, too!
So I love 'em both!
[ROSIA] By the way,
while we were filming,
Tsukino's idea
became a new flavor!
Now it'll always be on the menu!
[JACKLYN] To go along
with the TV commercial,
we had a rad poster photoshoot.
[ROSIA]
Woo!
[CREATOR]
Nice height! I love it!
[HOLMY] I'm sorry, but her dive
was a little bit sloppy there.
It looked a little odd.
Hey, Rosia, you think
you can do it again?
I don't think, I know!
[JACKLYN, ROSIA] Check it!
Here's how it turned out.
Hey, Big Brothers!
You should totally
go to Midicians spa.
You can play, eat, and relax.
[ALL] Bring your friends!
Spa Resort Midicians!
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪