[MR. MAPLE]
Attention, everyone.
Today, I'd like to introduce you
to a new student who just
transferred to this school.
Let's welcome Rom.
Yo.
[MR. MAPLE]
I want you all to get along.
Be nice, and don't bully him.
I mean it, you guys.
Bullying will not be tolerated.
You know that, right?
Hey, are you listening to me?
All right, you asked me
to "step outside."
Now what do you want?
Heh. Don't you get it, buddy?
See, you're the new kid,
and you gotta learn how we
run things at this school.
So now, we're gonna rumble.
Huh?
Wait! Crow, stop it!
They said no more fighting!
You leave him alone!
Shut up, stupid!
Mind your own beeswax!
Oh, c'mon now.
You can't be serious.
[CROW]
Hey, you!
You'd better not
underestimate me,
you overgrown cat-tailed poser.
I will crush you.
[ROM] Crush me with what?
Your spiky cartoonish hairdo?
[chuckles]
Okay, you're gonna regret that!
[yells]
Wait. Shuzo?
[ROM] Is that the same Shuzo
I've heard so much about?
[ROM]
Hey, so if I defeat you,
that makes me number
one around here, right?
Yo, man!
We still have unfinished
business to take care of!
[ROM]
Huh?
Don't underestimate m--!
[sighs]
Wow. You pack
quite a punch there.
Tell me, what's your name?
You can call me Rom.
Now, show me what
you got, Blondie.
All right, but
you should know,
my power has yet to be matched.
[ROM]
Good, then it's a fair fight!
Hi!
Stay tuned to see
who wins this duel
on the second season of
Show By Rock , coming soon!
Hold onto your tails!
The main character transfers to
a super delinquent high school,
and after numerous clashes
with strong opponents,
friendship blossoms.
It's a passionate,
heartwarming drama.
And after that, the
hilarious, forever-young,
rowdy boys' battle show
The Crows comes on!
Get ready, guys!
Passion flows non-stop!
Make sure you watch!
I'm not kidding!
Way to miss the mark.
He does like to exaggerate.
Show By Rock is about
bands, of course.
In Midi City, where
music is everything,
tons of bands aim for the top
in this classic story
of rock star dreams!
I can't wait, pyuru!
Everyone, please keep watching
Show By Rock , meow!
Oops, I did it again.
[RETOREE gasps]
Thanks, y'all! We're
counting on your support!
Bye!
[ALL]
Show By Rock!! Short!!