[KAI]
Five, six, seven, eight!
[KAI, RIKU]
One, two, three, four!
--One, and two, uh, three--
--One, two, three.
Too slow!
Riku, you keep falling behind!
Sorry, Big Brother.
Then, one more time.
We have to get
this perfect, okay?
Kai, Riku, good morning!
[KAI, RIKU] Hi, and a very good
morning to you, Shuzo
[SHUZO] Heh. I see you're as
enthusiastic as ever. Good!
Your dauntless dedication
to learning these steps
is quite impressive!
I'm proud of you!
Wow, thank you very much!
Thanks, but I still need
to work a lot harder.
Since we finally got the
chance to be on your show,
I don't wanna mess it up.
Now, now.
You've got to have
more faith in yourself!
Yeah, little bro,
take it easy, like me!
Maybe Kai can share some
confidence with you, Riku.
He seems to have it to spare.
I'd be happy to share some!
Thanks!
Then you'd do well to take
some of Riku's carefulness
and humility.
[SHUZO, RIKU chuckle]
[knocking]
[ASST. DIRECTOR]
Trichronika, you're up next.
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku, I'm counting on you.
Now, let's get out
there and boogie!
With the glittering star
steps of you twins,
and my shining
morning star turn,
together we'll create
an infinite rainbow!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
[SHUZO] Shuzo's Dream Galaxy
Absolutely Dance Studio!
Hey, everyone!
We'll start Shuzo's Dream
Galaxy Absolutely Dance Studio
with a twinkle in our toes!
Today's dance step is a
simple and classic one,
and the king of all the basics.
Here comes the box step!
Are you ready?
One, two, three, four!
Come on, guys!
Viewers watchin' at home,
why don't you give it a try?
Now!
It isn't your skill, fancy
costumes or even your looks
that will make a dance sparkle,
it's your gorgeous,
happy smiles!
Now, let's go!
Yay! Yay!
Five, and six, and seven! Yay!
[KAI] Wow, you're the coolest
guy in the world, Shuzo!
[RIKU] We're so lucky to
know Shuzo. He's the best!
--[KAI, SHUZO] Yay!
--[RIKU] Jazz hands!
[growls]
Hey, I was watching that!
Shut your mouth!
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪