[PLUM]
Chop, chop, lemon drops!
My name is Plum Arisuriver.
I will be giving you a
special lecture today.
It employs the method
acting technique
I learned in exotic New York.
Now, this is no exaggeration
that today's topic
is the most important one
we will learn at this school.
It's a critical life skill
every girl needs: Coyness!
Me!
[PLUM]
Oui , Rosia?
I, Rosia, will do
my absolute best
to remember everything you say!
Three hundred points!
Bravo, bravo, I say! Her
focused gaze! Her tilted neck!
And her salute is just
flawless! Très bon !
Ici , take a closer look.
The palm of her hand
is turned inward!
A salute is how one shows
respect to others.
But hers is a bit different.
It says she won't show all
her cards to the group.
A stubbornness she hides,
while seeming
outwardly friendly.
Perfectamente !
Wow, really? Gosh, thank you!
I didn't really think about it,
though, it just happened.
There! Five hundred points!
The uncalculating innocence she
commits to through the end,
how delightfully coy!
A hundred twenty-three!
If you'd said "okay," you
would've earned a mere 32.
Can you explain what you mean?
I got this.
If you'd answered
"okay" with emphasis,
that would have ended the
conversation right there.
But your answer made you
sound unsure of yourself,
so it leaves things open-ended.
Do you know what I mean?
They'd probably think,
"Oh, I wonder if she understood.
Is she all right?"
When that happens,
it means you've directed
all their attention
straight to you.
[JACKLYN]
Ohh.
[ROSIA]
That's it, Jacklyn!
[JACKLYN]
Huh?
Just now, you covered your
mouth in surprise, didn't you?
You're in luck, because I
just happened to put that move
in my little handbook,
136 Coy Poses !
It's one you should always use
when something's really funny--
or, of course, when
you're actually surprised.
[PLUM]
Ser gute , Rosia! Jawohl !
I totally see.
[ROSIA] Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Be careful, Jacklyn.
There's a fine line between
being coy and being a phony.
But how will I know
the difference?
I don't know if I'm good
enough to pull that off.
[ROSIA]
Tsukino! That's totes perf!
See? You did even more
than just say "I can't do it."
When you pout like that,
you're also showing the person
that you're so not happy
about the situation,
which is way critical to
get your point across!
By the way, that's
in the book, too.
[PLUM] Rosia-
chan , you're super sugoi !
[ROSIA giggles]
Um, I didn't plan to do that,
it just kinda happened.
This girl will rule the world!
[ALL]
Huh?
There it is.
My point has been made!
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪