[music playing]
I wanted you to hear how
beautiful this sounds.
Do you wanna give
playing it a try?
Oh, no, I have no musical
ability. I couldn't.
Don't worry about it.
I'll teach you!
[A]
My word.
This must be the "fun"
Master was speaking of.
Thank you. You've helped
me understand something.
I accept your kind offer,
and would like you to
teach me the shamisen.
I'd be happy to! And I have
a favor to ask you, also.
You have so much courage.
Would you mind sharing
some of it with me?
It would be my honor.
I am called A. And you are?
My name is Un. Nice to meet you!
[stomach growls]
[A grunts]
[A chuckles]
[BOTH chuckle]
This Dango is simply delicious.
Yes, it's the best
in the Far East.
[OUTLAW] Hey, that looks pretty
good! We'll take some o' dat.
[OUTLAW GANG laughing]
They never learn.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[DARUMA]
Water.
I'm utterly parched please.
[UN]
Uh.
Um, here you go.
[A, UN gasping]
[screams]
It's a yokai ! A really
big yokai ! Run--
[DARUDAYU] I feel much
refreshed, thanks to you.
I sincerely hope neither
of you girls were injured?
You-You were inside the daruma?
Um. Thank you for saving us.
Pardon?
You speak too softly;
I cannot hear.
[A] Excuse me! If I may,
what is your name?
As the whispering wind wills,
and at my own whims,
I wander the lands
creating my own journey
as a daruma drummer.
Dear girls, my name is Darudayu!
[giggles]
[NARRATOR]
And this, my friends,
is how the band Tsurezurenaru
Ayatsuri Mugenan
fortuitously came to be.
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪