[A grunting]
Good, that's enough.
Yes!
[MASTER]
Hmm... Excellent swordsmanship.
You put your soul into it.
[A]
Yes, sir.
[MASTER]
However...
You're not having fun!
[gasps]
Your words are wise, Master,
but will adding fun truly help
me defeat my adversaries?
[MASTER]
Hm...
When you know the
answer to that...
...you'll have the strength
to defeat anyone!
[A]
What is this "fun" he speaks of?
I'm not familiar with
the concept of it.
When I know the answer
I can defeat anyone?
[music playing]
Ah. Welcome! Come in!
No, that's all right.
I was just, uhh--
Go ahead. Take a look around!
We have the best selection
of any store in town!
We even carry some
rare and exotic items!
What instrument are
you looking for?
[A]
Sorry!
[UN]
Huh?
[A grunting]
[laughs]
Where you goin' with that
pretty little toy, huh?
Nowhere! Just please let me by!
[OUTLAW] No can do,
'less you wanna hand over
that pricey lookin' shamisen!
Sorry, but I can't
let you have this!
[OUTLAW]
Then we got a problem.
[A]
Let her go.
Preying on the weak and
innocent, that's deplorable!
Shame on you!
If you're so tough, fight me.
[OUTLAW]
Impertinent little imp!
As if you could best the great--
[OUTLAW]
Aw, forget it. You bore me.
You'd better remember this!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Oh, thank you.
I don't know what
I would've done
if you hadn't shown up just now.
Hey, wait. Aren't you the
girl from the other day?
And you are the girl from the--
[UN]
The instrument shop!
Wow, how lucky!
This is meant to be!
Come back with me! Please!
[A]
Uhh...
Whaa--?! It's over?
Man, I hate cliffhangers!
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪