[TOKIKO]
It's Tokiko's R-R-R-Room!
Hello everyone,
I'm Tokiko Shirosugawa.
Today, we have a--what do
you call it?--"girl group"
with us in the studio!
Our first guests, Plasmagica!
Thank you for coming.
And thank you very much
for having us here!
Pyuru!
[TOKIKO] I have a whole
mess of questions for you,
but first, time
for a commercial!
[ROSIA]
♪ Summer means ♪
[ALL] ♪ B-b-b-beach,
b-b-b-b-beach... ♪
Hey, Big Brothers!
You should totally
go to Midicians spa.
You can play, eat, and relax.
[ALL]
Yay! Spa Resort Midicians!
If you don't come, I'll cry.
And you don't want that, do you?
[TOKIKO]
How you doin'?
The group with us today
is from the famous
and prestigious label
Banded Rocking Records.
Well, that sure is a
tongue twister, isn't it?
Yes. Y'all feel free
to call me Chuchu.
I'm on lead guitar,
and vocals too.
[TOKIKO]
"Antique Batman."
Oh, I get it! Like a
purple bat. That's cute.
[gasps]
Uh, hi my name's Retoree.
Call me Retoree.
I play bass or whatever.
[TOKIKO] Now, "Blue Station."
Like a train station?
[RETOREE]
Uh, no, not exactly.
I play the drums, and I'm Moa!
[TOKIKO]
Here's "Super Cosmo"!
I bet tons of stars
come out of it, right?
[MOA]
Pyuru!
[TOKIKO]
And who are you, kitty-cat?
Me?
Uh, hello, I'm on
guitar and vocals.
Thanks for asking, meow.
My name is Cyan, meow.
[gasps]
[TOKIKO]
So tell me, girls,
are "pyruu" and "meow" the
hot catchwords these days?
Pyuru-ru-ru!
[TOKIKO]
Excuse me, will you stop that
while the cameras are rolling?
And here's your axe:
"Strawberry Heart."
Oh, that shade of pink!
It's perfect for you.
And now, ladies, if you
would please stand up.
--[CYAN, CHUCHU, RETOREE] What?
--[MOA] Pyuru?
[TOKIKO] Look at that!
Isn't everyone cute?
That curlicue kills me!
Uh, thanks?
[TOKIKO]
So small and fluffy!
Yeah.
[TOKIKO] So your tail and
heart are connected, then?
[TOKIKO]
Delightfully poufy!
Its own weight
keeps it straight!
[RETOREE]
So embarrassing.
[TOKIKO]
Well, that was fun, wasn't it?
Pardon, can we talk
about our music soon?
[music plays]
[TOKIKO] Oh, I'm so sorry.
We're outta time!
Once we saw your tails,
that was really the end!
Today, the lovely girls
of the fabulous Plasmagica
were our special guests, meow!
Bye-bye, see you all
next week, pyuru!
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪