[TOKIKO]
It's Tokiko's R-R-R-Room!
Hello there, it's me,
Tokiko Shirosugawa.
Today, our lovely
guests will be making
their third appearance
on the show,
and I couldn't be happier.
Still the biggest draw in Midi
City's entertainment world,
welcome the boys of Trichronika!
[SHUZO]
Hi!
[screams]
Goodness, it's been far
too long since last we met!
I know. It feels
like an eternity!
I thought maybe you'd
forgotten about me!
'Course not. I could never
forget my precious Tokiko.
As if anyone else could, either.
But really, we're just so
thrilled to be back on the show!
It's another chance to shine!
Twins! C'mon, don't
be shy. Say hello!
[KAI, RIKU]
Hi!
I'm Kai, the drummer!
Thanks for having me!
I'm the bassist, Riku!
It's great to be here!
Cut to commercial, please.
The melon flavor is my
favorite! What's yours, Kai?
Well, I like the
grape one the best!
How 'bout you, Shuzo?
[chuckles]
My favorite: Rainbow! Hooray!
--[KAI] Ah!
--[RIKU] Wow!
[ALL]
Dream Galaxy Rainbow Pop!
To get another box,
just find a shining star!
[TOKIKO] Now, I'm certain
they need no introduction,
but who cares,
here's Trichronika!
Hey!
[TOKIKO]
How you doin'?
Can you tell us what
you're up to these days?
Yes.
So, coming this fall, we're off
on a journey of the cosmos,
called the "Rainbow
Galaxy Tour"!
[KAI] We'll take off
from Sound Planet.
[RIKU] And visit other planets
around Sound Galaxy!
[TOKIKO]
Oh, wonderful!
Wait, does that mean
you won't be performing
in Midi City for a while?
I'm sure your fans will be
absolutely devastated
about that.
[SHUZO chuckles]
No need to worry.
We'll be streaming our concerts
to all the folks in Midi City.
So everybody wins!
[TOKIKO]
Be still my shell!
Besides, no matter where I am,
you all know my heart
is ever with you.
Yes!
The twins' sparkling stars,
and the gleam of
my morning star,
combined with the raging
adoration from our fans
will create an infinite
rainbow in the whole sky!
I wanna taste the rainbow!
[KAI, RIKU]
Bravo, Shuzo!
Well, everyone, we had
a fabulous time today!
Thank you, and goodbye!
[CYAN] ♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
[ALL] ♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪One, two, three, yeah! ♪
♪ Always singing ♪
♪ From the heart, you can't
stop a song that's ♪
♪ From the heart,
passion overflowing ♪
♪ Feel the beat of the
music we make ev'ryday ♪
♪ Come and join the PARTY ♪
♪Clang-clang!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪Bang-bang!
♪Woo-woo!
Do-re-mi-fa-PARTY! ♪
♪ One, two, three, yeah! ♪