Ugh...
I'm so sick of this heat.
It isn't even pleasant to eat outside anymore.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
But at least we have that really
strong sunblock to put on, right?
You did put the sunblock on
before coming outside, right, Sissy?
Huh...? Why would I?
Are you a dermatological idiot?
Ultraviolet rays are the skin's enemy.
You don't want your beautiful, creamy
white skin covered in freckles, do you?
But we won't let that happen, now will we?
Just hold still while I rub this
over every last inch of your body.
Uh, no thanks.
Come on, there's no need to be shy,
Sissy. I only want to look after your health.
Koroko, quit it!
Knock it off!
Shirai?
Oh, hi there, Wannai.
And Awatsuki, too...
What's up?
Actually, we wanted to ask you a favor.
Swimsuit modeling?
Yes! The swim club is involved
with this swimsuit manufacturer.
They've been insisting we do this for them.
Apparently, it'll be in the
upcoming issue of their web catalog.
The older girls in the club are
all busy competing in a swim meet...
which means we're the only ones available to participate.
This is perfect! We have to help them out, Sissy.
Hmm...
Me wearing a swimsuit and modeling?
It doesn't sound like something I'd be good at...
I don't know...
Of course. We totally understand.
Thanks, I'm sorry.
I thought better of you than this!
These poor girls are in desperate need of our assistance.
Yet you refuse to volunteer your time?
How uncharitable!
I'm tearing up... it's so tragic!
Hey! You wanna chip in?
All right. If you don't think I'll
be too bad at it, I'll help you out.
That's the selfless Sissy I know!
I'm so glad!
Yes, thank you! We really appreciate it!
Excellent!
I get to spend a whole day with Sissy in a swimsuit!
I gonna have to pick out a really sexy bikini to model...!
Yes! I'll have her salivating!
I know there are dirty thoughts going through your head.
I give! I give! I give! I give! I give!
I didn't know it was such a big business!
It's exciting and intimidating all at the same time!
Uiharu!
It's great that you were able to get
your friends to come along, thanks again!
It was no problem. With something like
this, the more the merrier, don't ya think?
Eh, so after seeing us, are you sure
you want us to play swimsuit models?
Don't worry so much.
Modern fashion designers have come up with
all sorts of ways to make even underdeveloped
bodies look more appealing to the eye.
Thank you for your support, Shirai.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Who is she?
She's the manufacturer's general manager.
Thanks for coming today.
It's gonna be great...
Uh... weren't there two more coming?
More models?
Well, hello, Shirai.
Ugh... I know that voice.
Oh, my, look at all the people who are with you!
Is this a social studies field
trip for school, or something?
Oh, hi there, Kongo.
And Konori's here, too!
What do you have to say for yourself?
Why are you wearing that outfit?
The school rule dictates that we
wear our uniforms even on days off.
Or have you forgotten that?
For this afternoon at least, I am no
mere student of Tokiwadai Middle School.
I am here as a model...
Naturally, I dressed as such.
A model?
They asked you, too?
Huh? You don't mean... are you?
Did you come for the swimsuit modeling as well, Konori?
Yeah. I ran into a classmate at the gym, and
she asked me if I'd be willing to come today...
What about you guys?
We've got some friends in the swim
club, and they asked us to help out.
It's obvious that none of you have
done anything like this before...
I'd be delighted to give you a pointer or two.
From a pro! I've been modeling
ever since I was a little girl.
The thunderous applause echoing off all the walls...
the cheers screaming my name!
I can still hear their ardent admiration, even now!
Give me a break. I bet the only
person cheering for you was your mother.
Now, shall we get down to business?
Will you show me to the changing rooms?
Uh... sure...
Right this way.
I must be dressed in a suit that flatters my curves.
Is that girl an acquaintance of yours?
She's more like somebody I wish I wasn't acquainted with.
All right! Everybody please
choose whichever swimsuit you prefer.
Okay!
Hey, look... what do you think of this?
Wow! that's a really pretty one.
Oh! This one's really cute.
I think I found one I like, too.
Hmm... This doesn't look that great...
and I don't care for this one... Hmm...
Haven't you decided on a suit yet?
It seems like you could use some tutoring.
Why don't you allow me to select one for you?
I don't need your help, thanks.
Halter-top suits are best for those with a nice bust...
and then there are triangle-top bikinis, which
always work well, whether you have the goods or not.
I said no thanks. Now go away.
It's obvious which one you'll need.
You have my sympathy.
I look forward to sitting you down and having
a nice, long chat one of these days, Kongo.
Wow, look what Misaka found.
It's so cute!
Oh, yeah. Frills and polka-dots work so well together.
No, you've got it wrong...
I don't want to wear this one or anything...
I'd love to see you in that one! It's
perfect. I know it'll look adorable on you!
I agree! What's the harm in trying it on?
I don't know...
I don't think it's the right fit.
Don't be like that. Give it a chance!
It'll look great.
No doubt in my mind!
You really think so...?
Well, if you guys insist, I'll give it a shot.
Oh, nice... I take it you prefer
designs that look more child-like, Misaka?
No! Of course I don't. I was just browsing...
Here... this is what I want...
I'll just take it over here and try it on.
Um... what's wrong...? Was it something that I said?
Why do I have to be so embarrassed about the stuff I like?
I... I feel practically naked wearing this thing.
We're all girls here, Uiharu.
There's nothing to be shy about.
Plus that looks great on you!
It does? Really?
A bikini divides the eyeline between top and bottom...
but a one-piece shows off a woman's entire figure...
so they only flatter truly slender people.
Oh... Is that swim club knowledge?
Do you have any other pointers
for picking out a suit to wear?
Well, let me think...
sarongs are an option...
they are, of course, fashionable...
and they're also useful for covering the lower body.
It's not like I was trying to hide anything.
I just thought it was cute!
Sorry for taking so long.
I am a little disappointed that all the
designs they had were so tame like this.
But given that these are off-the-rack
swimsuits, what more can a girl expect?
I don't know what to say.
We probably shouldn't be surprised.
Uh... individuality's important in a model.
It sure is.
Modest as it is, I'm sure this
must be driving you crazy, Sissy.
I know it'll be difficult, but please, try to resist!
I don't think I'm gonna have a hard time with that.
Oh, look at you girls...
Is that all you're working with?
Well, what do you think? Impressive, huh...?
I'm working the "sexy and exotic"
angle. I expect rave reviews.
It's the ultimate swimsuit experience for the audience.
That's a snake!
It's not so scary, I think it's cute!
Her name is Ecaterina.
Oh, look at that. What a pretty python.
You do realize it's a snake not a dog, Don't you?
Would you hurry up and put that away already?!
Oh, why?
Don't you want to play with this little cutie?
What do you think, Shirai. Surely you're not scared.
What? Me?
I think it's just a tasteless stage prop.
It's a little bit tight...
but it's all they had...
They don't carry larger sizes.
Oh, wow!
It's nothing but an empty room.
This is where we're going to be shooting? It's so bare.
This high... tech studio digitally
creates any number of different settings.
Wow, that's amazing! I can even touch it.
It's the latest in Academy City technology.
Oh... I was just wondering-is the
person shooting us going to be a man?
Yeah... now that you mention it, that's a good question.
Even if he was a professional, it would still be kinda...
you know? I can't stand amateurs...
Don't you people get it? The whole point
of modeling is to be seen at your sexiest.
All the photography is automated.
The camera will never be inside your field
of view, so you don't have to worry about it.
Just act naturally, okay?
She said to act naturally and
nothing about that looks natural to me.
Come on, Sissy. We need to play our parts, too.
What parts do you mean?
Oh, you know...
You're the sexy beach babe I apply suntan lotion to.
Not this again! I said no!
Aww! Just a little, please? You'll like it!
Go away!
Rub... a... dub... dub!
No, no, no!
I get it now. That's totally natural for them.
Yeah, that's Misaka for you...
She always sets a great example.
What do you guys think? Should we follow her cue?
Yeah!
W... where are we now?
Wherever it is, it's incredibly cold.
When the scenery changes in the room, the
temperature changes, too? That is high-tech.
I think this may be taking it a little far.
We're supposed to be relaxed and
natural in the middle of a blizzard?
That's what makes a real model...
Whatever happens, you get the job done.
Serves you right for being such a show-off.
Ow! Hot!!
From too cold to too warm.
Way, way too warm.
Why'd they program in such extremes?
Water! Water!
Not this much water!
Like I said, what's with all the extreme weather?
If they want to put us on a boat,
can't they at least make it comfortable?
Not bad...! A prize barracuda!
Sorry... I think that's just a really big tuna.
Is not!
Maybe you should let her have her fantasy...
I'm sure she doesn't want
credit for something she didn't do.
Oh, I guess we're off the boat.
Wow... the stars are beautiful...!
And over there!
Looks a lot like the Earth!
Huh?
Great, we're on the moon, now?!
Well, at least it's pretty.
Yeah. Very pretty.
Hey, you guys, look!
What's that over there?
I'm sorry. Please hold on a moment...
We need to make some adjustments and change the scene.
Great. What are we in for this time?
A campsite?
I'm sorry.
We're experiencing some technical
difficulties with the cameras...
We should have it taken care of soon...
In the meantime, why don't you take a short break?
So, what do we do now?
Oh, by the way, the food there is real.
Feel free to cook something up if you want to.
Cook something up using this stuff?
What should we make?
With the number of people and the ingredients we have...
We need to make some curry!
Some of us can work on the
curry, and the rest can do rice.
I'll be on team curry!
Yeah, me too, please.
All right. Why don't I take the rice.
If you're making rice, Sissy, that's what I'm doing!
Ugh... please...
curry is such a boorish, unsophisticated food.
What are you talking about? It's delicious.
You really don't like curry?
I'm betting you just have no idea how to make it.
Please! Don't be ridiculous!
I have a recipe for the best curry.
It's been passed down through
the Kongo family for generations!
Oh? What kind of curry is it?
An authentic family recipe? I'd love to try it!
Yes, please make it for us!
Well, since I'm stuck here anyway, I suppose I can
make do with whatever plebeian curry dish you all prefer.
We can make a normal curry and your dish.
We've got lots to work with.
That's a great idea!
Okay let's do it! Yeah?!
Well...
if you insist, I guess we can.
Hooray!
All right... everything's settled then...
We'll go and get the rice started.
Right!
Be ready for something amazing!
Um, excuse me, Kongo...
Oh...! Yes?
Would you mind if we joined you?
We'd love to see how it's done.
Uh... certainly, if that's what you want.
Shall we get started cooking, ladies?
First... why don't we...
uh... peel these onions?
Sure!
Stupid thing.
It's broken?
This isn't working, either.
I know!
This is what I call induction cooking!
Don't talk to me.
I have to concentrate, or it's gonna boil over.
Could you do this one, too?
What? Don't tell me there's more!
You get a lot less onion after all that peeling, huh?
So, what are we supposed to do with this?
Oh... well, we, uh...
That's what those things on the side of the plate are!
Out of the whole entire onion
they only use this one tiny part?
It must be a precious ingredient for all that work.
Well... feel like you're learning some things?
Yes!
Thanks...
I mean that.
This is a great experience.
It's so nice of you to teach us.
It's embarrassing to admit... but neither
one of us has ever made a curry dish before.
It's an honor to learn from someone so talented.
Now the carrots...
Do we cut them into quarter-rounds?
Huh? I think for curry, they're supposed to be in chunks.
But quarter-rounds will look more appealing on the
plate, and besides, they'll cook faster at that size.
Oh, Uiharu, don't you know anything?
The key to a good curry is that the
vegetables are neither too big nor too small.
When we make curry at home, we chop the
veggies up smaller so they blend in with the sauce.
No, no, no!
You've got it all wrong!
You want the vegetables to be
large enough to add some substance.
Making it taste good is the bigger concern.
It tastes just fine my way!
Let's settle this.
The vegetables should be cut in bigger chunks, right?
No, chopping them up is better, right?
Okay, now I'm confused.
They're grating the corn?
Tomato skins, interesting.
They're pretty hard to peel, aren't they?
And now we're adding seaweed?
Also unexpected...
and difficult to cut up, too.
We leave the peel on the tangerine...
And slice it into rounds...
Ah! I got juice in my eye!
Ow. That doesn't sound like fun.
I wonder what the finished product will be like.
I'm just excited about trying
the first curry I've ever made!
The ingredient choices are all so unique!
I never would've thought of adding burdock root.
Or strawberries...!
Ah... all this cooking is making me hungry!
I can hardly wait!
What's wrong?
What is it?
Um...
The truth is...
well...
You see, I...
I've never actually made this curry recipe before, okay?
In fact, it's not just this...
I've never done any cooking.
I'm sorry...
It would have been too embarrassing
to back down after what I'd said.
Well, in that case...
we can ask the others to tell us how to make it.
Yeah?
I'm sure they wouldn't mind.
Do it, Sissy... do it, Sissy.
You can do it, yes you can...!
You can do it. Yes, you can!
Yeah! Time to eat!
Here we have chicken curry!
Which is accompanied by a lovely seafood curry.
Looks great!
Okay, everybody ready to eat?
Absolutely!
Mmm... It's delicious!
You know, you really can still
taste the little vegetables.
It's nice to have big ones in there, too!
I'd say we did a pretty good job, wouldn't you?
Yep. I couldn't agree more.
This is great, isn't it?
It was worth every bit of effort.
Y... Yes.
See?
It tastes better because we
all worked together to make it.
You know, you seem like a nice person...
What's your name again?
Oh, um... I'm Mikoto Misaka.
Misaka? That sounds familiar...
Well, in any case...
I've decided to give you the
opportunity to become my friend...
How does that sound?
Uh, that sounds great...
Thanks a lot.
Sorry for the delay.
The system is up and running,
so we'll resume shooting now.
Huh? Already?
Oh, you can continue eating...
I think we can get some great shots of that.
Mmm... that was fantastic!
I'll model anytime if we get to eat like that.
It really was a lot of fun.
I'm so glad you all had a good time today.
I suppose eating peasant food
isn't so bad every once in a while.
You did have seconds.
Hey... where's Misaka?
Where'd she run off to?
Let's see here...
No, that's not it...
Maybe this one?
This bathing suit is adorable!
Now then...
Woohoo!
That looks like Zapper...
what is she doing? Weird.
I'm ready for my close-up!
Who's there? You would dare to assault
Mitsuko Kongo of Tokiwadai Middle School?
Um, I hate to break it to you, Kongo,
but you're not actually in the next one.