Kuroko!
Use of your abilities inside the dorms is prohibited...
How many times do I have to say it?
Right, Misaka?
Give me a break.
What an old bat...
All she ever talks about is rules!
Well, that is kind of her job description, you know.
Is there nothing we can do to
make her chill out a little bit?
I was just teasing you yesterday; it's
not like I was doing any harm to anyone.
Why am I always the one she
chooses to vent her frustration on?
I'm telling you, she's a bitter old maid.
I wouldn't let her hear you say that.
That's the truth of the situation, though, isn't it?
She's the head resident of a girls' dormitory,
a job that offers zero contact with men.
No wonder she's still single.
But she shouldn't take it out on us,
it isn't our fault she's heartless and alone.
That was just her, wasn't it?
Yeah, but what is she up to?
There's something off here.
She's dressed like a normal person.
Now that you mention it, I've noticed that
she goes out somewhere whenever she has time off.
To meet a man!
Huh?
Come on. This is the perfect opportunity!
Kuroko, where are you going?
So... do you have a plan, here?
Oh, yes. We're going to follow her
and get leverage to use against her.
Leverage? Like what?
It must be a blind date...
I can't imagine that somebody would willingly go out
with such an inhuman harpy after actually meeting her.
Although, whoever set her up must be quite a gambler.
What are the chances of this
matchmaking foray turning out well?
Oh! Perhaps her date lost a bet
and has to go out with her as payment.
I think that's taking it a little far.
Odd place for a blind date.
I see now.
Her mystery man must be Italian...
An Italian man named Marco!
Okay, now you're just making stuff up.
School District 13...
All this way?
What on earth is she doing here?
How long do you plan to follow her, anyway?
Until I get to see her darling Marco with my own eyes.
Yes, of course. "Marco."
Ah... hey look, Auntie's here!
Best be careful who you're calling Auntie, young man...
If you want some of this yummy
food, you should call me Big Sister.
Wow! It's pizza!
Now, now, there's no need to push.
I've brought enough for everybody.
No way.
This is Asunaro Park Children's Orphanage...
It says here that this is a Child Error facility.
Huh? That's the term they use for kids who
are left in Academy City without any family.
As always, thanks so much for coming.
It's nothing.
The little ones always look forward to seeing you...
"When's Big Sister coming?" they ask.
I'm sure I enjoy it more than they do.
The help you give us is priceless...
I can't tell you how much we
appreciate having you volunteer here.
I hope you'll continue coming for a long time.
Yes, I will.
Big Sister, you're gonna eat with us, aren't you?
Just try to stop me.
I've never seen her act like this before...
She's so happy.
This is unusual indeed...
I never would have guessed that this is
what she'd choose to do on her days off.
To think I had no idea that the noble Head Resident had
such a tender heart buried underneath her rough exterior.
"Noble"?
Compared to her, we are selfish children...
I am ashamed to think of all the horrible things we said.
calling her a bitter old harpy!
Idiots!
Uh, you're the one who said all that...
Hold on...
It's not fair for them to make us do community
service because we had lousy test scores.
This could be a valuable life experience.
Besides, it's fun playing with the
children and seeing their smiling faces.
Yeah... I guess you're right about that.
Oh... excuse me... do you have a moment?
I want to introduce you to our director...
Saten, Uiharu, this is Miss Kazuko Shigenomori.
It's a pleasure to meet you...
Are these two girls students of yours, Daigo?
They are.
I want to thank you in advance for all your help today.
Not at all. We're happy to be here.
By the way...
are those two over there friends of yours by any chance?
Huh?
What a coincidence running into you guys here, huh?
Are you guys volunteering, too?
Oh... um... y'see...
Hey... isn't that the head resident of your dorm in there?
Did the three of you come together?
Oh, no... Certain circumstances
led us here, but I won't go into it.
Okay... nicely done, everybody.
Hello!
It's nice to see you again.
Oh... it's nice to see you, too.
A couple of my students came to volunteer today...
They're new, so they might make some mistakes...
Please feel free to tell them if they do.
Oh, no, no...
I'm sure that none of your
charges could do anything wrong...
Don't be silly...
Plus... I don't have much experience
when it comes to scolding students.
Wow... I had no idea your head resident volunteered here.
Maybe Mr. Daigo asked her to help out.
The man she's talking to in there is called Mr. Daigo?
Yes, that's his name. He's our homeroom teacher.
Finally, her mystery man has been revealed to us.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Isn't it obvious? Our head resident has
fallen head over heels in love with him!
Wha... In love?!
I have a mission.
I will see to it that her love does not go unrequited...
I will not fail her!
I don't know about this, Kuroko...
I do! I think it could be a lot of fun.
I'll help, too. She deserves a happy ending!
You guys're getting on board with this idea, too?
I hope you realize it's not going to be a simple task.
Fortunately, Shirai has a devious
talent for creating romantic situations.
How about I give you a smack on the head?
It's no good to ask after you've done it...
That wasn't nice.
Okay, that's enough standing around...
Let's hold a strategy meeting!
Oh, noble head resident...
We welcome you home.
What do you think you're doing?
You do not care for a moist towel?
Then please allow me to take your bag for you.
Oh, look at that...
I see you've chosen a higher-end beverage than normal...
Did something special happen today?
What kind of joke are you playing?
I don't mind punishing you again.
No joke, ma'am.
Helping you in your time of need is my only desire.
If you have anything you need to get
off your chest, you can confide in me.
Anything at all!
Discuss my personal life with you?
No way, not a chance...
Don't be absurd.
Forgive me...
I only want to be of service to my noble role model.
I can tell when you're up to something, Shirai...
What is it?
I'm not up to anything at all...
I'm sorry I've given you reason to think so.
It's just that today I had the chance to
see you playing with the poor young orphans,
and I gained so much respect for you!
How do you know about that?
That's not even the half of it.
I know about Mr. Daigo, too...
Right? We know it all?
Oh, uh... well... Uh... huh!
All right, you! What exactly do you know about Daigo?
Won't you let us help you this once, Head Resident?
Help how?
We could play the part of Cupid for you and Mr. Daigo.
Wouldn't that be great?
No! Never! Why would I need Cupid?
Besides... I'm not even interested in Mr. Daigo.
Ma'am surely you do not want to
deny the true desires of your heart.
That would be tragic!
You may as well admit that what you want
from Mr. Daigo goes beyond friendship...
It's no use saying otherwise.
I can see right through you.
While you're little, what gives you the right to say that?
It's been twenty-nine long years.
Hasn't the time come to know the joys of love?
Isn't that what you deserve?
Just... go away!
Are you sure you want to spend
the rest of your life as an old maid?
K... Kuroko...
If you let this chance pass you
by, you may not get another one...
I have my own experience with unrequited love.
Please, Head Resident, allow me to
help you make your dreams come true!
Er... don't you think that's enough?
Eh?
You mean it?
This isn't just some trick?
You really wanna help me?
Yes. I really do.
Eh...
Huh?!
These lovely girls have volunteered
to play with you this afternoon...
Let's give them a nice, warm welcome, okay?
It's nice to meet all of you.
What a great turnout...
I'm so glad your students could come along...
You must be really proud of
them for volunteering like this.
Oh... yes... I'm very proud.
Mr. Daigo!
Yes?
What is it?
So... what's this brilliant plan for me, Shirai? What now?
You just relax and take it easy for now...
Your love life is in very capable hands, I can assure you.
All right. We're going to put
the plan into action immediately.
So there is a plan?
Oh... well...
Mission accomplished! I've got
her all settled in the kitchen.
Good. Excellent work, Saten...
With that done, phase one of
the plan is officially complete.
On to phase two.
In which we get the head resident
and Mr. Daigo alone together.
Having them participate in a collaborative
activity is a surefire way to bring them closer...
Our plan needs a name...
"Operation Fruits of Love" is now in effect.
"Fruits of Love"? Are you sure...?
Doesn't that make it sound improper?
Well... the fruits of love are children, aren't they?
Hey, Big Sisters...
Come play with us!
Well, you heard the girl, Sissy...
Why don't you go and play with them?
You remember us discussing this part, don't you?
Oh... well, okay then.
All right, everyone! Let's go!
Oh, Shirai... what am I...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Daigo, hi... Why are you?
Well...
I wanted to come help you with the cake.
I have to admit, I'm really impressed that you're
going to make a cake from scratch for the birthday party.
Homemade is always better.
Well... uh...
Well, how about I get started on the icing?
I know I don't look it, but I am
fairly good at cooking... or I try.
There's something about baking a
cake from scratch that feels so homey.
Oh... Yeah...
It may sound silly...
but this is the kind of thing I love.
It's so fulfilling... the act of creating something.
Sorry, I realize I'm blabbering...
but this is so nice.
It's just... I'm hoping to get married someday...
and standing in the kitchen like this
with my wife is a favorite daydream of mine.
I wonder how they're getting along so far.
Come to think of it, we just assumed that
things were going to go well between them...
What do we do if it doesn't go as we planned?
Well, you see...
Hey, that sounded like the head resident, didn't it?
What in the world?
Calm down.
There's nothing to worry about...
Naturally, I made sure to prepare contingency
plans should anything unexpected happen.
Ah! What's going on? It looks like something exploded!
What is all this?
Uh. I can explain.
It was all my fault...
I was trying to open a bag of flour, and it just...
All of this from opening a bag of flour?
Hey... It'll be okay...
We can start over...
No problem... Right?
Right... thank you, Daigo.
Unfortunately, there isn't enough
time for that before the birthday party.
So, maybe you could run out and get us a replacement cake.
Oh... I guess you're right... Okay...
If you could wait one sec.
Our noble head resident here knows of
a cake shop that should work perfectly!
Sh... Shirai!
It's fine. Don't be nervous...
These two will go along with you for moral support.
You're coming?
Yes! We're at your service!
Hurry! Run away!
This is crazy. What am I doing here?
Hah! I caught you!
Yeah... I was no match for you...
and I guess that means it's my turn to be "it."
Now... run!
Run as fast as you can, or I'm gonna catch you!
I would do anything to save them...
Anything in the entire world!
The whole city can hate and revile me. I don't
care! I'm not going to let anything stop me now!
Child Errors...
Huh...
Happy Birthday, Meg and Kei!!
Hip, hip, hooray!
It ended up being a big ordeal.
First we went the wrong way...
Then we got chased by a dog...
And nearly fell into the river.
How could that happen?
You were just buying a cake.
Well... who cares?
It turned out all right in the end.
All right, everybody...
Time to dig in!
Yeah!
This is nice, huh?
Everybody's having such a good time.
I'm sorry...
I... I wish I could've been more helpful today.
Oh, hey...
I haven't seen you without your glasses.
It looks nice.
Oh... I mean... you look good with them on, too...
but you also look pretty when you take them off.
Look at that! They're being
all lovey-dovey with each other!
Hah! Lovey-dovey!
Hey! You shouldn't be teasing grownups like that!
That's just silly...
For one thing, I'm certain that your Big
Sister would have no interest in me whatsoever.
I've got an idea.
How about you describe your ideal woman for us, Mr. Daigo?
Huh... well, let me see...
Someone I could respect, I guess.
Someone you can respect, huh?
And what would that require?
Well... she would really have to be somebody who
puts the needs of others before her own, you know?
Earthquake?!
Right... okay... everybody stay...
Listen up! Everybody take cover under the table.
Good! now stay there and keep qui...
Be careful!
Has it stopped?
We've had a lot of these lately.
Thankfully it was small...
We'll be fine.
Oh, no!
Miss! Are you two okay?
Young man! Didn't I tell everyone to get under the table?
Yes... I'm sorry, Big Sister.
It'll be okay. Are you sure you're not hurt?
Oh, wow.
You were fantastic.
You have my respect.
No, really... it was nothing.
You were fantastic.
You have my respect.
No, really...
And so...
I would like to marry you.
Say yes, and we'll cook together forever.
Yes.
I am so sorry.
I know I was out past curfew.
These things happen...
Just try to be more punctual next time.
That's unbelievable...
I've never seen the head resident
overlook a curfew infraction before.
It was inevitable, I suppose. Love changes a person.
Yes, hello...?
Oh! Daigo!
Huh? There's something you wanna ask me?
And you're sure you want me?
It has to be me, you say?
All right. I'll be there.
What does he need to ask her so urgently?
Isn't it obvious?
After today, there's only one thing it could possibly be.
Huh?
He's going to propose?
I can't believe it's really happening!
This is so exciting, I can hardly stand it!
Why would he choose a family restaurant like this?
It is pretty pathetic...
I'm guessing he's never had a girlfriend
before so he doesn't have any idea what to do.
Obviously when a man proposes to a woman,
it should be at sunset in a fancy,
romantic restaurant on the beach!
No... a rooftop restaurant with a view of the city...
Right... Misaka?
Yes, and then...
after she's accepted his gallant proposal...
they climb on top of a mountain
and watch a fireworks display!
That's going a little far.
What?
So, anyway...
You said there's something you wanted to ask me?
Yes... I guess I should just come right out and say it.
Yes?
I was wondering...
How would you feel about marrying
somebody who is younger than you?
M... Marrying...
Someone... younger?
Yes... for instance...
someone like me.
I've got you now!
Well... I, uh...
I don't really think age matters...
not as long as you respect the person.
I knew it...!
I figured you would say that,
but I just wanted to make sure.
Sorry for calling you out of the
blue to ask you something like that.
No...
Congratulations! Way to go!
You mean you were watching?
Head Resident, I knew you had it in you!
Now, you'll need to pick a venue...
and meet his parents...
and then honeymoon!
Shirai... I would appreciate it if you
would give me a hard pinch on the cheek.
Huh?
If this is all just a dream, I'd like to wake up now.
Well if you insist.
Okay. That's enough, Shirai.
Before you go...
There's one additional favor I need to ask of you.
I, uh...
I want to give him a proper answer.
Around and around and around and around...
Hello, Daigo...
Do you... have a sec?
I can't put my finger on it, but there's
something different about you today.
Um... about our conversation the other night...
Yes. I really appreciated that.
I finally have the courage I
need, and it's all thanks to you.
Oh! What's this?
I'm going to propose to my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
That's right.
And your girlfriend is...
Yes...
I was nervous.
But then you said age doesn't matter
as long as you respect the person...
and I knew you were right.
I can't tell you how grateful I am to you.
Sure.
It's no problem...
I'm glad I could help.
Congratulations...
I wish you all the best.
All right.
Aww... I was sure it was going to work out for her.
That's a shame.
I bet she'll find someone else before long.
Of course she will.
She's a great person.
Okay, everyone!
What are we going to play today?
No fair! I couldn't've been more than a second late!
It doesn't matter if it's an hour,
a second, or a tenth of a second.
Whatever the case, you broke curfew.
I hope you're prepared to answer for that, Shirai.
Kuroko!
Kuroko!!
Now, Head Resident, I know you've suffered a
major disappointment, but don't let it get you down...
Just think of those children looking up
at you with their sweet, angelic faces...
Mow them down!