Hot, hot, it is so hot in here.
Come on, wake up...!
Please, open your eyes, Sissy!
Sissy!
Wake up already...
Okay, well maybe a kiss will help, then...
This isn't a fairy tale, ya know.
But it did work. You're awake now, aren't you?
That's unexpected...
Why are you two still here?
Yeah, well, there's something we needed to ask you.
I find it unbelievably hot in here...
It's the middle of summer.
Shouldn't they at least turn
on the air conditioning for us?
You do make a good point.
I'm very sorry, but we had a power outage last night.
Things haven't been restored to normal quite yet.
All right, then...
They're using emergency power for
basic operations and critical patients.
Again, seriously?!
Your solution to this is to take off all your clothing?!
Well... it's really hot in here, y'know?
We're not alone. There are people everywhere!
What if I just leave my underwear on?
No, not going to work.
Alright.
Dr. Kiyama, we're really interested in
your opinion on these patients as a specialist.
I'd be happy to help you...
but it's so hot in here.
Saten's running really late.
Got on the blue stripes today, huh?
In your email you said you wanted to show me something.
That's right, and I can't wait anymore.
This thing is so incredible.
I've finally found the elusive
item we've all been looking for!
Ta... da!
That just looks like a music player to me.
It's what's on it that really matters.
Just wait... I'll show you later, okay?
Now, I'd like to pick up where we left off,
if it's okay...
Why are swimsuits acceptable and underwear is not,
when both expose the same amount of skin?
No.... that isn't the point.
This "Level Upper"?
Can you tell me what kind of thing it is, exactly?
What does it do...?
How is it used?
Unfortunately, we don't know.
No details so far...
but it might have something to do with the
students who have fallen into comas recently.
That's what you think, yes?
Right.
So... why bring this problem to me?
Well, I've been giving this some serious thought lately...
It seems that elevating one's ability
might well disrupt normal brain function.
If that's the case...
I think we'll need help when we find this thing...
and I feel that your professional
experience could be invaluable.
This is something I would be happy to help with.
I am a cerebrophysiologist...
it's my area...
Aside from that...
there is something else that's been bothering me.
Who are those girls?
Oh... so you're a brain doctor?
Are you here to look at Shirai's brain?!
We are conferring with her about the Level Upper matter.
Well, if that's the case...
This is pretty serious...
Anyone found in possession of
it will be taken into custody.
Isn't that a bit extreme?
The investigation is ongoing,
so I can't tell you everything...
but it does seem that its users suffer some side effects.
Anyway, I find the users of
any drug usually turn to crime.
Saten, is there something bothering you?
Oh...
no. Not at all.
I'm so sorry!
Please don't worry about it.
It just got on my stockings,
so once I take them off...
How many times do we have to tell you not to
take your clothing off while you're in public?!
Look at me for a moment.
It's not like I'm anything particularly special...
No man in here is going to care about seeing my body.
Everyone has different tastes, so you can't really know...
Besides which, it's not only men
you should be thinking of, you know?!
I know you're busy, so thank
you for giving us this information.
No... I thank you...
This has reminded me of the time when I was a teacher.
I've enjoyed it.
I didn't realize you'd been a teacher before.
I was once...
Bye.
I don't know what to say. She's a little different, huh?
Aren't you a little different, too?
All right then...
I think it's time we headed back to the office now.
That's a good idea.
and we should put whatever data
we have together for Dr. Kiyama.
Yes, you're right.
Okay guys, so we're all ready to
head back to the branch then, yeah?
Where did Sissy go?
I don't want to give this up.
It's not like I've used it yet.
So I don't have to tell anyone.
But I worked so hard to find it.
Are you okay?
Misaka! Why are...
Well, you disappeared so suddenly.
I was a little bit worried about you.
Oh... it's nothing, really.
Are you sure?
Oh, well... It's just that you know, it feels
like everybody is involved in this case other than me.
I'm not Judgment or anything.
Thanks you didn't have do that.
You've always got that thing hanging from your bag.
Yeah... I guess I do.
I got it from my mom.
It seems silly, huh...?
It's not as if good luck charms are scientific
You're gonna be an Esper, Sis! That's so cool!
Sweetheart...
I need you to know...
I'm not totally on board with this.
Mom's a big worrywart, huh?
I'm just concerned about her.
I don't want them messing with her head.
It's not like that at all, Mom!
I want you to take this.
A good luck charm? That's not scientific!
No matter what happens, you can
always, always, come back home...
I want you to know,
you're more important to me than anything else.
At the end of the day, my mom is just superstitious.
It's not like something like
this can protect me anyway, right?
It's not as if it's magic.
It sounds like your mom is really nice...
What I mean is, she cares enough about
you to give you a charm like that, right?
Yeah, she's a good mom.
But even still, sometimes I feel like
I'm not living up to expectations...
It's been all this time, and I'm still only a Level Zero.
Aw, Saten, really...?
Does your level matter that much?
How is it going?
There's a lot of code and jargon
here, so it's hard to know for sure,
but I think I've managed to uncover some sites
that look like they're Level Upper exchange spots.
Good job, Uiharu!
A list of presumptive places.
Wow, there sure are a lot of them, aren't there?
Hey, what are you doing?
It has to be one of these places, right...?
So, if I go through them one...
by... one, I'll find it eventually.
Level Upper, huh?
It's everything I've dreamed of...
Something that will finally make me an esper.
But I don't know anything about it,
and that scares me...
What if it isn't good?
You said you would give it to me!
Where's the Level Upper?
The price has gone up.
If you want this, it's gonna
take another hundred thousand.
Could you just give me my money back?
Please, just stop!
Quit whining and give us the money!
Is he a test to see how elevated your levels are?
Need to know how far you've come, huh?
I should really call Judgment or Antiskill.
Aw, great! My battery's dead!
Really...
what can I do?
There are three of them... and
I'm barely out of grade school...
What can I possibly hope to accomplish?
I'm a level zero...
how can I help in a situation like this?
You leave him alone!
Can't you stop? He's already hurt...
and Antiskill will be arriving at any moment!
'Scuse me... What did you say?
You've got a smart mouth on you, don't you, kid?
But you also don't have any power.
so what right do you have to tell me what to do?
You have power, so you think you've earned it.
Well, I've got news for you: you haven't.
So leave her alone...
You're a bunch of pathetic losers with no power at all!
And I am an officer of Judgment!
Shirai's here?
I'm placing you under arrest for aggravated assault.
Now cooperate.
Ha...! You've got to be kidding me, here!
One more little kid to deal with isn't gonna a problem.
You should really be more careful...
I've been running around the city for hours already...
and then I finally find what I'm looking for
and it's a bunch of thugs assaulting my friend.
What are you talking about?
It looks like I'm going to be
hazardous to your health today.
Interesting! Quite a skill.
Teleportation, huh...?
I never seen that before.
It almost seems like you're disinterested...
but you're very much involved right now.
Before the Level Upper, we used
to be scared of you Judgment types.
But there have been some pretty
big changes lately, you see...
We're stronger.
And now that we've gotten stronger...
we'd like nothing more than to pound
you and people like you into the ground!
Too bad you're going to lose to...
He vanished!
He came from behind me.
He must've sneaked up somehow.
I don't think I have much choice!
I'm going to have to use these on him.
I... missed him!
First I have to figure out why
I can't anticipate his movements.
Yep, that was a different direction than I expected.
That was pretty cool, I have to say...
You cracked, what, one, two ribs?
What do you think you're doing now...?
Aw, don't tell me you can't teleport anymore.
I'm not through playin' just yet.
What, are we playing tag, now?
It's fine if you wanna run away,
but that just means the other two
are forfeit... the girl and the fatty...
I'll just kill them.
This building is scheduled for demolition...
I probably won't be able to
find anywhere safe to hide in here.
I don't hear anything...
no footsteps.
Okay... at this point, he should
still think I'm on the first floor.
Ah! Found ya!
Funny story: one of our hangouts
happens to be in this building...
so I know every last little nook and cranny.
And in here... sound resonates.
Hey, kid.
you heard what I said about sound, didn't you?
You can spend all your time
tiring yourself out and runnin' away.
I don't think it'll take very long.
I'll get you soon enough.
Seems like you're finally tired of playing tag.
All right, girl.
let's take care of this.
I kinda pity you.
Your life is going to end before you
even know what ability ultimately did you in.
I know more than you think...
You have the power to mislead
peoples' visual perception...
You distort the light around you to
make it show what you want it to show.
You figured it out.
Your legs swing around at an impossible angle.
Things I throw trace an impossible trajectory.
Basically, you project the image
of yourself to a different location.
So my focus is diverted to a different area...
and my attacks end up missing your actual body.
That explains it.
The pins I threw curved...
Because of you!
Heh... Enjoy.
I call it Trick Art...
So what now?
How do you plan on fighting against my power?
You have nothing to rely on but your own eyes.
Perhaps...
Maybe what you say is true, and I can't hit you directly.
Huh? What are you trying now, girl?
Here's the thing about teleportation...
It means I have the power to displace
matter from one place to another.
One example of this is my ability to cut through
these steel... reinforced columns with window glass.
Look, this is your final warning.
Drop your weapon and surrender...
If you refuse, I can't guarantee your safety.
Give up? Are you kidding me?
I'm not the one who should be surrendering here.
It's sad really...
I wish our situation didn't have to be this way.
But unfortunately you're leaving me with no other option.
You should say your prayers.
'Cause at this point,
I'm afraid I have no choice but to crush you.
your little light trick isn't going to save you this time.
What the hell d'ya think you're doing?
Do you know what will happen after I destroy
all the columns that are supporting the building?
You can make a guess, can't you?
You wouldn't! No way!
You can't do this!!!
I was a little worried I may have overdone it a bit,
but... hah...
it was scheduled for demolition
anyway, so I guess it's no big deal.
Now... I'll be taking that Level Upper from you. 'Kay?
Aw, do you wanna cry?
We can go demolish some more buildings if you would like.
Are you kidding me?
The best you can do is hand me a music player...?
Please, don't be ridiculous.
But the Level Upper, it,
it's a song!
Wha-what did you say?
That's some good work... We'll take over from here.
Gosh... I'm so glad Shirai is safe.
I feel this way...
but I'm not proud.
She's a friend...
She's my age...
We are so similar in so many ways, but
she happens to be Levels up from me...
and it hurts a lot of the time.
How can a Level Zero relate to an Esper?
I wish I knew.
Ruiko!
Hey!
How's it goin'?
Akemi? And Mu,
and Mako, too!
What are you doing here alone, studying?
Yeah, I guess you could say that...
What about you guys?
Just studying at the library.
We can't change our ability levels,
but we still have to keep our grades up.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, hey guys, have you heard about this Level Upper thing?
Hold on what are you talking about?
Oh I know,
It's the thing that's supposed to increase your ability.
Yeah, yeah...
and I heard someone say that it goes
for a lot of money on the black market.
Well, I don't have any money!
Um... hey, you guys...
I have one...
you know...
I've got one of them.
Maybe I was trying to pretend I
was okay with not having an ability.
And maybe I was wrong...
Saten! Please, no!