You know what we should do?
We should go see a movie today.
What do you think?
A movie? Yeah, maybe.
Here, this looks like a good one, doesn't it?
It's called "Caught Between Love and Youth."
Yeah, sounds okay...
I guess I like a romance flick as much as the next girl.
Oh, really?
You don't sound all that interested.
I don't care one way or the other.
We both have the day off.
I thought we could do something together.
Hey! It looks like they're having some kind of
summer festival on the rooftop over at Seventh Mist.
Oh? My guess is it's just some
silly event designed to amuse children.
We won't know for sure unless we see it, will we?
Uh... well, I mean...
it might be nice to try something
new every once in a while.
Oh, I see what it is...
This is what you're really interested
in checking out, isn't it, Sissy?
It's not! I couldn't care less about some stupid thing...
No need to be ashamed, Sissy...
You can tell me if you like Gekota.
It's all right.
I told you, I don't care!
Sorry I'm late!
I hope you haven't been waiting for too long.
I missed the first bus.
No, no, don't worry about it!
We only just got here ourselves.
Hey, Saten's not with you today?
Oh... well, you see...
Man! Extra classes on a day off?
That's a dirty trick for them to play.
Yeah... and it's not just our
middle school that's doing it, either.
They're calling students together from all over
to participate in some special workshop for the day.
A workshop?
That's right...
I don't know what makes it special, though.
Well, special or not, it's bad luck for poor Saten.
Such a beautiful day to be stuck in class.
This is it... at least I think so.
Let's see here...
Hey! Ruiko!
Akemi! Mu! Mako!
Hey, guys.
What's with making us climb all these stairs?
I'm exhausted.
Don't be such babies. We just got here.
Yeah, well...
It was a whole lot of steps!
This way, then.
Honestly, this is the worst...
Going to some school on our day off
to take extra classes, and for what?
It's not like they're gonna teach
us how to raise our ability levels.
That would be too easy, wouldn't it?
Normally, I'd be sitting by the pool right now.
And what about you? You were planning to
hang out with Uiharu today, weren't you?
Well... What choice do we have?
What're we gonna do with you, not even putting up a fight?
Oh, come on...
You won't even complain a little?
You're hopeless.
Hey, we've got a long day ahead. Be nice!
Well, the quicker we get started, the quicker it'll end.
Let's hope so.
They really did pick people from all
different schools for this, didn't they?
It sure looks like it. That may be the case.
But this is still a lousy turnout.
It's so much easier to doze off in
class when there are more people there.
What's with the long faces?
You all look like your puppies just died.
Why did we come to this thing, anyway, Boss...?
It's so lame.
Well, we're here, so you might as
well quit your griping you got it?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you!
Scary...
They look like they're in high school.
Quit staring! They'll notice us.
No, no problems here.
Please, just take it easy.
Yes... got it.
Okay, kids, that's enough.
Let's all get inside now.
Yeah? Who're you supposed to be?
I'm your teacher for today.
Our teacher?!
I'm Komoe Tsukuyomi and I teach the morning class here.
If you want to smart off to me, I will
happily extend the lessons even longer.
One thing is paramount if you wish
to further develop your abilities.
And that's the achievement of Personal Reality.
Today, we're going to go back to the basics
and really explore exactly what that phrase means.
Personal Reality involves the
development of a reality unto oneself,
separate from that which may be accepted as true reality.
As we study this concept, we must also look at
the quantum theory and the uncertainty principle
postulated by Heisenberg.
We must study theoretical physics because Personal
Reality and quantum theory have something in common:
both are rooted in probability.
Okay, unless anybody has questions,
that should conclude the morning lecture...
I'm sure you'd all like a nice, long lunch break,
but please don't be late to the afternoon class.
It's for your own good, I promise.
Ugh.
I thought lunch would never come...
Hey... massage my back, would you?
Do I have a choice in the matter?
That feels so good!
You're becoming an old lady.
Oh, shut up.
We've been here for so long.
I can't believe the day's only halfway over.
This is seriously draining.
Yeah, it is...
Oh, now that you mention it...
don't we have to go to physical training this afternoon?
We sure do.
Oh... and what's even worse you guys
know the teacher they put in charge of it?
From what I hear, she normally does this with Antiskill.
Eh?!
That is bad...
I bet she's gonna make us run some really harsh drills.
I wanna go home!
Well... sitting around here's not gonna help anything...
We might as well eat while we still can.
What is it?
I forgot to bring lunch with me.
Everyone else has the day off.
Hey, it's me...
No, they're not open...
I'm gonna go out and grab something.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Saten.
So... long time no see...
Jufuku, remember?
Oh... uh... hi Jufuku...
Are you taking the workshop this afternoon, too?
Yeah, I am.
Sorry, I didn't notice you.
I didn't really want to be noticed...
Have you forgotten my Dummy Check ability?
It comes in handy when you don't
want people to realize you're there.
You made yourself disappear?
No... My level isn't high enough to manage that...
but I do have a knack for making things seem less present.
Oh... I get it.
Uh... Saten?
Huh? Yes? What is it?
I wanted to say thanks for always
answering the letters I wrote you...
I really appreciated it.
Oh... sure...
no problem...
I did promise I would.
But, uh...
Well... it would mean a lot to me if
you would write the next letter first...
maybe?
Uh... Well...
if I get a chance...
It might sound silly, but I sleep with the postcards
you send me tucked under my pillow every night...
I like feeling close to you,
even if it's only in my dreams.
That's... very sweet.
You know... I'm so glad I came today...
I was really dreading coming to
this stupid "special" workshop...
But it turns out I was wrong, though.
Since I got to see you.
Hey... you... you know...
um, if you feel like it, maybe we can eat lunch together.
Oh... I can't...
I forgot to bring one, and the cafeteria's closed...
So I'm gonna have to go out and pick something up.
That's okay...
I mean, I actually packed way more than I can eat today.
You're welcome to have some if you'd like.
Oh... thanks, but...
Wow! You're sure you don't mind?
Not at all.
Please help yourself to whatever looks good.
Okay, thanks a lot.
You made this? It's delicious!
You think so? I'm glad to hear it.
You know...
It felt really awkward sitting in that classroom...
almost like I should be ashamed or something.
Why do you say that? We're all in the same boat.
Well... That's kinda the point, isn't it?
They've gathered together a certain type of people.
I wonder if there will be more workshops...
for people like us.
Maybe...
but even if there are more of them...
There's nothing we can do about it.
There's nothing we can do.
It's hot out here.
I can't believe they're making us work out in this.
Isn't this some kinda abuse?
Can you do anything but complain?
You think whining's gonna make it any cooler? Huh?
Sorry, Boss!
Seriously scary.
What did I tell you earlier? Don't stare at them!
Okay, look sharp, people...
In case you haven't guessed,
I'm your physical training teacher,
Miss Yomikawa...
Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you too, Miss Yomikawa.
All right, that's enough of that.
Why don't we get started with an endurance run?
It's too hot!
No way!
Not up for testing your limits?
Slow down, Ruiko.
You should be conserving your strength.
I don't get why we're even doing this in the first place.
It's not fair.
What's the point in making us run until we drop...?
Torture?
Hey, you three!
Stop dragging your feet.
I know you can go faster.
When you don't think you can run
any farther, then raise your hand.
She's enjoying this.
Keep moving!
Yomikawa runs her classes like a drill sergeant...
Hang in there, kids. You can do it.
Get through this...
and you may overcome something greater.
Run!
Get up! On your feet!
I can't do it.
I can't...
You giving up?
Yes, ma'am. I give up.
All right, make this last lap a sprint.
Huh?!
I said, sprint!
Just hang in there.
You're almost done now.
Okay, very good...
How about going for one more lap?
I can't run anymore.
Get up.
Get up and give me one more lap.
You call this training?
I certainly do.
How can you? All you're doing
is putting her through the ringer!
Why not go ahead and call this what it is...
It's punishment! Admit it, lady!
The whole point of this
so-called workshop is to punish us!
It's nothing of the sort.
Then why do you have us running
until we're too exhausted to move?
The point is to teach you how to overcome your limits.
Look at him.
He was the first one to raise his hand...
yet he's still running.
When you convince yourself you
can't do any more, you're finished...
Even though you may still have some
strength left that you're just unaware of.
Her, for instance.
So sure she couldn't go one more
step. until she ran another lap...
Where do you think the strength
to run the additional lap came from?
The same applies to developing your abilities.
What I wanted to teach you today is not
to decide so quickly what your limits are.
Oh, please!
Don't give me that crap!
She's down! Are you okay, Boss?
You think we won't go after you because you're a teacher?
That will be all. Class dismissed.
You're running away?
Time's up for today.
Everybody hurry back inside!
Hey, Ruiko!
Come on! Hurry!
Quick, before you get soaked.
It should clear up by the time we're done here.
Aww, man...
after the last class, they're
gonna make us take an ability test...
We know how that one's gonna turn out.
"When you think you can't do any more, you're finished!"
Dead on...
Always nice to hear another empty pep talk.
You know...
maybe that punk girl was right earlier and this
workshop doesn't have anything to do with education.
Like I said: punishment.
First we all slip into comas, and then
they force us to take these stupid classes...
I wonder what'll be next...
They could at least have been straight with us.
Why didn't they come out and say we're being
punished instead of pretending it's a workshop?
I mean, come on...
was what we did even that wrong?
Who wouldn't want to level up so easily? In
this world, you gotta take every advantage you get.
Yeah, you've got a point there.
It's not right to cheat.
Um... Ruiko...?
We all cheated, so it's only natural
that we're being punished for it.
My, aren't you a good little girl?
You idiot!
Why did you challenge her like that?
Aren't you scared of her?
Yes... Terrified, actually...
Her eyes are like daggers.
Even so... you didn't back down one bit!
I swear I could see sparks when their eyes met.
Me, too!
Then there was that popping sound!
I think that was just thunder, guys.
I know what I heard.
Sparks or not, what Ruiko said was right.
It was wrong of us to cheat.
It was.
It appears that some of you may
have jumped to the wrong conclusion.
So before we continue, I want to clarify something.
Please understand this workshop was not intended as
a punishment for students who used the Level Upper.
Certainly, your actions were far from laudable.
It would've been better had you resisted the
temptation to use that device to augment your abilities.
However... we do not want you to feel a disproportionate
sense of shame or remorse for having done so...
As far as punishment goes, I'd say
slipping into a coma should suffice...
That's a far more harrowing experience than a workshop.
You've already paid for your transgressions the hard way.
So, instead of feeling guilty or bitter,
why not make the most of all you've gone through?
The Level Upper gave you a taste of
power that you've never had before.
However, that power didn't come from some device.
It was already inside you, waiting to come out.
As I'm sure my friend Miss Yomikawa would tell you...
"You convinced yourselves you'd reached your limits,
but... you overcame them."
Okay then.
With that said, we'll begin
the last class of the workshop.
I want you to think about using the Level Upper.
Close your eyes if it will help you focus.
Concentrate on the time you used your power.
As clearly as you can.
Remember every aspect of how it felt.
Now, I want each of you to try to
achieve your own Personal Reality...
or at least reinforce the footholds
that you already have in place.
A new reality...
my own reality...
Concentrate.
So, anyway...
he told me to study up on "Personal Reality,"
but I just don't get the concept, you know?
Maybe it has something to do
with the power of our own belief...
The way we shape the assumptions we make about the world.
I'm sorry...
I came so close...
So close to losing something far more
important to me than some stupid ability.
I couldn't take it...
I was so tired of not having any power.
And finally, it didn't matter anymore
what lengths I had to go to to get it.
I understand.
But this doesn't have to be it.
You'll be fine, Saten... I know you.
You're too stubborn to give up easily.
Don't stay here and let yourself be defeated.
You are not defective.
There's nothing wrong with you.
So... don't give up!
Okay, everyone!
We're going to finish up the
day with a quick ability test.
Go ahead and pack up your stuff and follow us, please.
So, how did you guys do on the test?
My numbers were actually up a little.
No way! Mine, too!
But our levels are still the same as ever.
I know...! Let's go do something
to celebrate the workshop being over.
Good idea.
Hey... you coming along Ruiko?
Oh... I don't know. Let me think.
No... sorry...
Go ahead without me.
I've got something I need to take care of.
Like I thought. It's from Jufuku.
I'm so glad we got to spend
time together again today, Saten...
It was really inspiring.
Seeing you go lap after lap in the endurance run...
And the way you stood your ground with that scary
high-school girl when everybody else was afraid to...
Watching you be brave gave me more courage.
I'm gonna try to learn from your example...
I'll stop moping about things I can't
change and be strong like you, instead.
I don't think I'm all that strong.
Of course I wasn't going to do that well...
For now...
I'll just keep trying.
Oh... hey... how's it going?
Pretty good.
All right! Done for the day. It's time to go home.
All finished, Saten?
We wanted to come by and pick you up. How did it go?
What was the hold up?
You took so long coming out of there, we
thought you'd already left and headed for home.
You should have seen it, Saten. Without you, we
weren't able to decide on a single thing to do.
Yeah? Then what've you been up to all this time?
So, Saten...
how does going to the movies sound?
Huh? Forget that.
They're having some kind of
event on the roof at Seventh Mist...
Doesn't that sound fun?
Well, I...
Do you really want to see Gekota that badly?
I told you, that isn't it!
So, you see, we've been split between two ideas.
We spent the whole day at the restaurant talking it over.
And... you want me to pick?
It's the movie, right?
Hey, Kuroko! No fair!
Okay! I say we go to the pool!
Eh?!
But that wasn't one of the options.
All right then. Why don't you decide Uiharu?
Huh?
Seventh Mist, right?
No, the pool!
What? Armed gunmen are hunting down Espers?
This is the work of the gang known as Skill Out.
What should we do, Konori?
Konori...
did you hear me?