You understand nothing!
I would do anything to save them.
Anything in the entire world!
The whole city can hate and revile me. I don't
care! I'm not going to let anything stop me now!
Hey... what's wrong?
Oh, gosh... what's that?
A fetus...?
It's no use. Every single camera has gone dead.
My phone's not going through, either.
Kuroko!
I can't just leave Sissy alone out there!
How can you help her with all these injuries?
Well, I...
You need to have more faith in Misaka.
I'm sure she can handle it.
A fetus...?
Is this the "Metamorphose" skill?
I've heard about it.
I guess it's real.
This is bad...
It's getting bigger.
Hurry, Misaka!
Why are you here, Uiharu?!
Uiharu! You okay?
Yes... I'm fine.
You're lucky.
You shouldn't have come down here!
Yeah... I'm sorry.
But, I...
Just stay there.
I'm not sure what this thing is,
but if it wants a fight, it can have one.
It's not after me.
What, then? Is it just on a random rampage?
Look at it.
It's almost like it's in pain or something.
What's happening?
The patients!
They all suddenly started going berserk.
We don't know why!
Have they regained consciousness?
No... They were in the same comatose state as usual.
And then, this.
All at the same time?
As if on cue...
They're all exhibiting the same symptoms...
They haven't regained consciousness, it's more
like they're all experiencing the same horrible dream.
Good grief!
What the hell is going on?
Hey, what is that thing?
A monster?
Some new kind of bio-weapon?
We'll have to do what we can with the men we have left.
Use of live ammo is authorized...
Fire!
Look...!
I think... it's getting bigger!
How incredible.
Who would've thought something
like that could ever be created?
I can just imagine the recognition I'll get from academia.
The network is utterly out of my hands at this point.
That's it...
I no longer have any hope of bringing
back all those children I helped to destroy...
They're lost forever.
Please! You can't give up now!
Is that an AIM diffusion field?
It's most likely a collection of them...
Yes, that's it...
Although I think it would be more
appropriate to call it an AIM burst.
The AIM diffusion fields of ten thousand people...
all bundled up together within the Level Upper network.
They acted as the catalyst to bring to
life a monster of latent consciousness.
Simply stated...
That thing up there is a collection
of ten thousand children's thoughts.
Academy City.
All my dreams were going to come true here.
I was going to be a powerful Esper.
But now...
My dreams have become a nightmare.
It doesn't matter how hard I try...
In this city, if you have no talent, you have no power.
So I'm stuck with my miserable, ordinary life.
A life where every day means being beaten
down, taken advantage of, or simply ignored.
So what can I do?
I have no choice but to get my hands on it.
I can't keep living like this!
I'm so tired of being powerless.
In a way... I pity it.
What now? How do we go about stopping it?
You're asking me that question?
It makes no difference what I say...
You'll never trust me.
Then what about this?
You're the one who took my handcuffs off, aren't you?
That doesn't mean anything.
You can't possibly trust me just because of that.
That's not all.
I know you're sincere about wanting
to help bring those children back.
I can hear it in your voice.
I trust you.
I completely trust you, Teacher.
You heard it, too?
There might be a way.
Think about it...
The AIM burst is a monster
created by the Level Upper network...
If the network were brought
down somehow, that might stop it.
The Level Upper treatment program!
It might not work but it's worth a shot at least.
I'll find a way to handle that thing.
While I'm doing that, You get that
chip and whatever's on it to Antiskill.
Right, let's do it!
Incredible...
There are still people out there who
are willing to trust without any reason to.
Captain!
No... No!
No! Stay away!
What were you just standing there for?
That monster could've killed you!
Uh... who are you?
A civilian shouldn't be here! It's too dangerous!
Geez...
Everybody just has to call me a
civilian. It's starting to get old.
Whatever, just get away from here right now!
You're the one who should get going.
That thing won't come this way unless
you provoke it with more shooting.
Even so...
We can't just stand down and do nothing either.
Do you know what that is over there?
An experimental nuclear reactor.
What?!
Hey, what's that girl doing?
That's her!
The girl Kiyama held hostage.
She sure is taking her time getting away.
She's not.
Uiharu's not being held against her
will anymore, and she's not getting away.
I need to ask a favor.
From now on, you're going to be facing me.
Geez...!
You're not going to make this easy, are you?
No!
Thank goodness! It's not broken.
I have to hurry...
Or it will be too late for everyone.
I can do this...
I'm a member of Judgment.
For them.
And for Saten!
You okay?
Honestly!
You kids these days do the craziest things.
Do you have the treatment program?
Yes, it's safe.
We'll cover you...
Hurry!
Damn! Another one.
Didn't you hear what I told you?
I said, you're going to face me.
I'm your biggest problem now.
So stop just standing there, looking all creepy...
Go on, make a move! Come after me, already!
By broadcasting the vaccine file throughout Academy City,
you will bring down the Level Upper network.
If the flower-haired girl can manage that,
It should succeed in bringing the
runaway AIM burst under control...
However...
It's starting to feel like this could go on forever.
Sheesh!
What do you want with a nuclear power facility anyway?
This is straight out of a monster movie!
Oh, yeah?
A collection of ten thousand children's thoughts...
Oh, no!
Yes, that's right.
We're out of time.
Take the file I'm sending and broadcast it
by all means possible throughout the city!
All right. The transfer is complete!
I'll take responsibility.
Just play it right now!
What is that?
Doctor! Look at the patients!
Whatever I have to do, I absolutely
cannot allow it to come any closer than this.
Music?
What is that?
Crap!
It won't matter how many times I
hit it if it just keeps regenerating.
It's not growing back.
That music must be the treatment program!
You did it, Uiharu!
Sorry about this... but it's game over for you now!
That was a closer fight than I like.
Don't relax.
This isn't over yet!
Hey! What do you think you're doing here?
No way!
The network may have been disrupted,
but remember, that's a mass of ten thousand
people's thoughts, created by AIM diffusion fields.
You can't think about it like an ordinary creature.
This isn't what we bargained for.
What am I supposed to do, huh?
The nucleus!
There has to be a nucleus where the
fields have become embedded somewhere inside.
That's the key!
Find a way to destroy it.
Is that it?
Was that Saten?
Are Level Zeroes permanently defective?
That's what they think.
I can't stand it.
It's hopeless...
As a Level Zero...
What's happening?
You probably...
wouldn't understand...
how miserable every day is for us.
You come here with so many expectations, and then,
nothing.
Stand back now...
Where you are, you might get hit.
What do I care?
I'm responsible for creating that creature...
Maybe you don't care.
But what about the students you taught?
Once we save them, don't you think
it's your face they're gonna want to see?
I'll help you save the children...
but I won't help you die...
You shouldn't give up so easily.
Got it?
I don't want you tangled up in that thing.
I'm the one who's going to tangle with it...
Right about now!
Incredible...
Is that the same kind of
induction field I was using before?
With power like hers...
maybe this will work.
The lightning isn't hitting it directly.
But the heat from the electrical impedance
she's forcing on it is blasting its body away.
When she was fighting me earlier...
that wasn't her full power at all.
Forgive me...
Anyone... would want to be... an Esper...
I should have realized so much sooner.
What's the use anymore?
I'll always be nothing.
There's no point.
I know how hard you were trying.
I was so tired of not having any power...
And finally, it didn't matter anymore
what lengths I had to go to to get it.
I understand.
But this doesn't have to be it. You can keep trying.
Don't stay here and let yourself be defeated.
You are not defective.
There's nothing wrong with you.
So... don't give up!
So that's it...
That's a Level 5.
It... worked.
Inspection of experimental reactor
core and surrounding area is complete.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Roger.
Do an additional sweep to make
sure no one was injured in the area.
Wait... uh...
What now?
What do we do?
About the children, I mean.
I have no intention of giving up.
I'll just have to try again.
It doesn't matter whether I'm
in a laboratory or a prison cell.
They can lock me up but they can't stop me from planning.
However...
I'm still not going to be choosy about my methods.
If you don't like the plan I come up
with, you'll have to come and stop me again.
Good grief.
She's never gonna learn, is she?
Sissy! Sissy!
Oh... Kuroko...
Sissy!!
I was worried about you! My
heart was aching the whole time...!
And look at you: Hair messed up,
scrapes and bruises all over your skin!
And I'm guessing you don't have
the strength left to shock, either...
I think I'll take this time to examine every inch of your
body for injuries and rub the soreness from your limbs.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I received a message from the hospital with good news.
It looks like all the people who used the
Level Upper are beginning to regain consciousness.
And we have you to thank for that...
Good job.
Now then, Sissy, let's pick up where we left off.
What are you doing? Knock it off!
I swear, if you don't stop this second...
There you are!
Oh, hey, Uiharu!
Don't "oh, hey" me! I've been looking everywhere for you!
Why aren't you in your room?
Are you sure you should be out of bed so
soon? There could still be something wrong.
You were in a coma!
I just took a long nap, that's all...
I'm totally back to normal now.
Including not having any kind of ability.
What is it?
I'm sorry...
for getting hung up on stupid stuff...
and for keeping secrets from you...
and for putting you through all of this.
You don't have to...
But I am...
I came so close...
So close to losing something far more
important to me than some stupid ability.
Oh, yeah...
I almost forgot.
I'm back!!
What did you do that for? Get back to your bed right now!
I was just thanking you for taking care of me!
Though, I think you should know,
even your panties are covered in mud.
That settles it. Things are officially back to normal.
How can you say that?
After everything I've done,
you're insulting my underwear?!
Is something bothering you?
Huh...? No, it's nothing.
"Can we really blame the people who used the
Level Upper for making the choice they did?"
"Maybe we're responsible for all of this; We
Espers, who didn't realize how much pain they were in,
how hard it must be to live here and not have an ability."
That's what you were thinking, or
something along those lines. Am I right?
Don't mimic me...
It's creepy.
That kind of compassion is just like you, Sissy.
And while we're on the topic of compassion, there's
one other thing I wish you would give some thought to...
and that is...
My feelings!
I deserve some love too, don't I?
I should thank you, Kuroko...
Your unrelentingly, unapologetically perverted
nature is giving me some of my strength back.
I'm serious here, Saten!
You are gonna get it...
Careful, Misaka!
Oh, dear! Shirai, are you all right?
Some things never change, huh?
After all we just went through,
isn't this kind of a cheap thing to do?
What are you talking about?
A swimsuit episode is perfect.
Here, tell me which one you like better...
Sissy, look!
I don't want to!