Who's back there?
I am Mitsuko Kongo of Tokiwadai Middle School.
Knowing that, will you still dare to attack me?
I'm so excited! We're going to the Garden of Learning!
I don't know why they gave it such a fancy name.
It's just the area of town where there's
a cluster of girls' schools, you know?
But they aren't just any ordinary schools.
The ones in the Garden of Learning are special.
They're all well-known girls' schools.
Tokiwadai Middle School is only one of them.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
We're only allowed in here today because
Shirai was kind enough to invite us.
If she hadn't, a student as lowly and
common as I am would have no business visiting
such an exalted place as this.
Could you please stop groveling?
You're starting to sound like a brown-noser.
Oh, hey. What is this?
Oh, I see now. You've got a page highlighted in here.
Is this a bakery you want to try
out while we're visiting, Saten?
Well, of course! It's the Pasticceria Manicagni!
Just read what it says.
"The cheesecake is a work of art, made from an authentic
Italian recipe and using only the finest ingredients."
I've always wanted to try a piece,
but the Garden of Learning is the only
place in the whole country where they have it!
You're more of a sucker for
advertising than I thought, Saten.
Next stop, the entrance to the Garden of
Learning. Repeat. Entrance to the Garden of Learning.
Uh... oh.
The bus got us here ahead of schedule, huh?
It shouldn't be a problem.
Three, two and one.
Wow! I've never seen weather forecasts as
accurate as the ones they have in this city.
The word "forecast" is so vague.
It's more accurate to say that they are readings
of future events established by precise calculations.
It kinda gets boring, though.
It would be more exciting if they
would slip up every once in a while.
Enough of that. Let's get moving!
We have invitations from Kuroko Shirai,
first-year at Tokiwadai Middle School.
I'm Kazari Uiharu.
And I'm Ruiko Saten.
Very good. Go on ahead.
This is such a charming area, isn't it?
Everything looks different from the rest of the
world, down to the crosswalks and traffic signals.
Pretty impressive, huh?
It really does feel like we're
tourists visiting a foreign country!
Yeah, it does.
You know, it kinda seems like
we're attracting a lot of attention.
Huh?
Yeah, you're right.
I bet it's our outfits.
I'm sure it's unusual for them to
see students who aren't from this area.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Whoops! Look at the time!
Huh? Oh yeah, you're right.
Come on. We should hurry.
It looks like they're running late, huh?
This is where we're supposed to meet them, right?
Yeah, it is.
They said that they wanted to see our school, so
it made sense for them to meet us by the entrance.
How inconsiderate of them,
keeping my Sissy waiting like this.
Oh, here they come now.
What happened to you?
Well, you see... I sort of slipped in a puddle.
Ah...
You asked for a quick change of clothes.
I'm afraid this school uniform's
the only thing I have to offer.
No, this'll be fine.
Does the size work for you?
Oh, yeah, it fits perfectly.
Though the skirt's a bit short, so it's a little breezy.
It's not fair you get to wear that.
Huh?
I know!
We should trade outfits!
What do you say? I think it's a great idea!
Yours is too small for me to wear.
Then, I'll go find a puddle to slip in.
Let it go already.
It will only be for a little while!
Give it up, Uiharu!
Aw, pleeease?
I sent your dirty uniform off to the cleaners.
Stop by there on your way home.
And if that doesn't work, we can
always have it sent to your dorm for you.
It's no trouble.
Wow. That's what I call service.
Do you have maids at your school, too? I bet you do!
I bet they come every day!
Oh, calm down.
Hmm... Maybe I want that strawberry crostata.
It looks good.
No, wait... That Monte Bianco over
there looks awfully delicious, too.
Ah! But how could I pass up that cioccolata?
Is it really that difficult of a decision to make?
Oh, not for me. I've already
decided on the cheesecake for sure.
Uiharu the sun'll be going down soon.
I'm sorry.
Just one more minute, okay?
Hold on.
Yes?
Huh?
Uh,
okay. Yes, I understand.
Is Judgment calling us in?
They sure are.
Go figure. Their timing couldn't
be any worse if they tried, huh?
We'll get yours wrapped up for take-out, Uiharu.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
We should probably hurry.
Yeah!
Always on the move, huh?
Well, I guess it's just us.
Uh, just a sec.
I need to use the ladies' room real quick.
Honestly! Why are they calling us in on our day off?
It's a Saturday!
Hey!
Ow!
No complaining. You can do that on your own time.
Yes, of course. Sorry, Konori.
So, are you going to tell us why you've called us in?
It began yesterday and continued overnight.
Six students, all from Tokiwadai.
They've been assaulted in a string of related attacks.
What's more, it's all been
happening in the Garden of Learning.
There's no one lower than a Level 3
Esper enrolled in Tokiwadai Middle School.
But these students are being targeted and
easily bested, which leads me to believe...
that the perpetrator must be a formidable Esper.
That is likely the case.
However, we don't know their ability.
Every victim...
was knocked unconscious using a stun gun.
And then?
What happened to the victims once they were knocked out?
I can show you the photographs.
It's not pretty.
I suggest you prepare yourselves before looking at them.
The tea is starting to get cold.
I've prepared for this sort of thing since
I first applied to be a Judgment officer.
The same goes for me.
Right.
In that case...
Hey, what's taking so long?
What happened?
Saten, wake up!
Targeting our school?
Oh yeah. She was wearing our uniform.
How's she doing? Is she all right?
Well, physically, it's nothing too serious.
She should be fine after she lies down for a bit.
It's just...
Have you zeroed in on any suspects yet?
No, not yet.
See, their particular ability is making it tricky for us.
Tricky in what way?
The attacker was invisible.
I'm telling you, it's true! I
didn't see anything when it happened!
Yes, but here. Take a look.
This is the image from the surveillance camera.
I don't care!
For the last time, I didn't see a single thing!
So the victims didn't see their attacker at all.
Naturally, our first idea was that it was an
Esper who could perform optical manipulation.
We made a list of forty-seven Espers.
They all have the ability to make
themselves disappear completely.
However, every last person on the list has an alibi.
Well, whoever it was showed up on
the surveillance cameras, didn't they?
Maybe it's something different than optical manipulation.
That could be the case.
Oh, a dove.
Eh?
Shirai, didn't you see it just now?
No, sorry. I didn't notice anything.
You didn't notice anything.
Uiharu, there's something I'd like you to try.
Here it is.
The ability's name is "Dummy Check."
It's the power to impair the awareness that
a person is looking at a particular subject.
Apparently, only one person has it.
Miho Jufuku, a second-year at Sekichu Middle School.
That's our attacker!
I don't think that's possible,
though. She's only a Level 2.
She's not strong enough.
According to her test results, she doesn't
have the power to completely conceal herself.
Man, I really thought we were on the right track, too.
What happened?
She's awake!
You should take it easy.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh!
Come on now. Just get a hold of yourself.
I understand. This has to be a shock.
If your bangs were a little longer, like this
girl's are, you would at least be able to hide it.
Who has long bangs?
Hey! It was her!
You mean you saw the person who did this to you?
That's right.
When it happened...
I saw this girl in the mirror.
First surveillance cameras, now mirrors.
So that's how it is, then. I think I get it.
She can make people unaware of her presence, but
only if they're looking right at her with the naked eye.
That girl made me look like a freak,
and now she's gonna pay for it, big time!
Let's do it, Uiharu!
Do what?
You've got some skills with that thing.
Yeah, well, I have to do it like this, or else the
terminals won't be able to keep up with the processing.
Anyway, the Garden of Learning doesn't fall under the
hundred and seventy-seventh Branch's jurisdiction, Kuroko.
Are you sure this is okay?
Our superiors have just given us the go ahead.
Now you're talking! Uiharu,
let's get this show on the road.
I'm on it. And, "Go."
There you have it, girls.
We are now connected to all two thousand fifty-eight
surveillance cameras in the Garden of Learning.
I'll find you now, creepy chick with the long bangs.
Just you wait. You're gonna get what's coming to you soon.
I still haven't forgotten that
cake you promised me earlier.
Do this and I'll get you a dozen of them if you want.
Yeah!
That's going to be too many.
Oh, you think so?
Really? Cause I don't see any harm in it.
We're not talking about cake anymore, you two.
Huh?
Uiharu, go ahead and exclude areas
E through H, as well as J and N.
Okay.
Those are the areas the furthest
distance away from Tokiwadai.
Since they're so far, students from
our school rarely have reason to go there.
I think we can go ahead and
exclude high-traffic areas, too.
Why do you say that?
The suspect's uniform.
Don't you think it would stand
out a bit in the Garden of Learning?
Yeah, it would.
Think she uses her ability whenever people
are around, even when she's not attacking?
Probably. Even so, she can't
possibly maintain it 24 hours a day.
Then she'll have to find someplace out of
the way so she'll be able to catch her breath.
Exactly!
And if that is the case, then...
You should put that away.
You were the one who gave me these ridiculous
eyebrows. I fully intend to pay you back with interest.
She really disappeared.
This is no time to be impressed. Go after her, Saten!
All right, I'm on my way.
Ow!
What just happened?
Something bumped into me, but I don't know what it was.
Coming through!
Be careful!
Here we go.
As you can see, I'm with Judgment.
I'm taking you into custody. Come quietly, or...
Yep. She was never going to come quietly.
Uiharu, could I get some directions, please?
Working on it.
Go out to the street, turn
left, then go up to Third Avenue.
Copy that. Thanks a lot.
Sure.
How?
This game has been fun.
But it's all over now.
Impossible. Why isn't my Dummy Check working anymore?
Who can say?
This is why I hate all you brats from Tokiwadai!
Nice try. But, you see, stun guns
don't really have any effect on me.
Uh, um...
And that was actually holding back.
Uiharu! Please contact Antiskill and inform them
that we have successfully apprehended the suspect.
Right.
Good work today!
One last thing to do.
So, what'll it be? What kind
of eyebrows should I give her?
No!
Oh, dear.
Funny looking, right?
Oh, well, uh...
Go ahead and laugh!
Laugh as loud as you can. Just like he did!
Just like who?
It was spring.
I was dozing off in the glorious midday sunshine.
In my naiveté, I believed that this time
of peace and comfort would last forever.
But then...
Spring came to an end.
It was so sudden.
Tell me why! Are girls from Tokiwadai really so special?
That's not exactly the reason.
Then what is it?
Well, your eyebrows are just so...
Weird!
I hated the boy who cast me aside,
and I hated the dumb girl from
Tokiwadai who took him away from me!
But more than anything else, I hated
the funny eyebrows that ruined my life!
And that's why I decided I would
give everybody funny eyebrows like mine!
Uh, what?
Yeah, sorry. You lost me about halfway through, there.
What's the matter?
Just go ahead. Laugh at me! You know you want to!
Um...
I, uh...
I don't think they're weird.
Not weird they're just...
um...
Yeah! They give your face character, that's
what it is. Personally, I really like them!
Now that's taking it too far.
I, uh...
Is it okay if I sent you a letter sometime?
That's fine.
Impressive.
She really could make herself disappear completely.
Now that you mention it, wasn't
she listed as a Level 2 Esper?
That is odd.
I wonder, could the info in the database be incorrect?
No, of course not!
What is going on here?
Oh? The other victims too, huh? Yes, I see.
Here's the thing. It's a special ink developed
by a university in the tenth school district.
They say there's no way it's
coming off sooner than a week.
What now, Saten? Do you want me to
get that cute hat ready for you again?
That jerk.
Stupid eyebrow girl! I knew I
should've drawn something on her!
Calm down, Saten! Get a hold of yourself!
What am I gonna do?
Hey, Uiharu. Have you heard of the sandal hag?
The sandal hag?
They say she's this ugly old woman
in sandals who chases after you!
Yikes!
And she's butt naked!
That's just gross!