Was that another earthquake?
There have been a lot of those lately.
Who's there?!
Beware, I am Mitsuko Kongo of Tokiwadai Middle Scho...
I heard there was another earthquake yesterday...
Was your dorm damaged at all?
No, we were fine...
Fortunately my place didn't really shake that much.
Hmm... That's strange, considering
you're in District Seven, and all.
Mr. Daigo...
Can I ask you... why I'm here?
Oh, of course.
Come on in.
A new transfer student is joining us.
I thought you two should meet...
since she's going to be your roommate.
I know it's late notice.
But as our school's Judgment officer, we thought
you'd be a good choice to help her get settled.
Oh...! Yes...! I'll do my best!
Thank you!
I'm Erii Haru'ue.
A transfer student from District Nineteen?
That's odd...
In the middle of the term like this?
Yeah, usually transfer students join at the start
of the year, or at least the beginning of a term...
What's gotten into you, Saten?
You seem really happy about this.
Well, of course I am! She's going
to be Uiharu's roommate, after all...
That means she'll be my friend, too.
Hey, Saten!
So, um...
I'd like you to meet Erii Haru'ue...
And Haru'ue, these are my friends.
On the right is Kuroko Shirai...
Next to her is Mikoto Misaka.
They both go to Tokiwadai Middle School...
And that's Ruiko Saten.
She's in our class.
Hello, there...
Uh... if you don't mind me asking...
Why's all your stuff just sitting out here?
Oh, yeah...
You see...
I was at the train station picking up Haru'ue
when we got the call that the movers
were already here with all of her things.
It wasn't very considerate of the
movers to just drop these here and go.
Well, we can't leave it all sitting here.
I can take care of that simply enough.
Oh! Why didn't I think of that?
Amazing.
I've never seen teleporting before.
That doesn't surprise me a bit...
Not to sound immodest,
but there aren't many teleporters with my
level of power, even within Academy City.
Okay, okay...!
Now... shall we get this all put away?
Yeah!
That's the last of it, huh?
Thank you all...
I really appreciate you helping me.
It's no big deal, really...
So anyway...
we finished sooner than expected...
Let's have some fun, huh?
Agreed!
Don't get too excited, Uiharu...
Geez, have you already forgotten?
We have that joint conference to attend today.
What conference?
Judgment and Antiskill are meeting this afternoon.
Supposedly...
it has to do with all the earthquakes
we've been experiencing recently.
A conference on earthquakes?
Yeah. We have to go.
Well... Misaka and I can still show Haru'ue around.
Without me? No fair!
It'll be fine.
They can meet up with us later, right?
It'll be okay...
Saten can be a bit too much to handle sometimes,
but Misaka's nice... and we'll
join you as soon as we're finished.
Too much to handle?
Saten, I want you to promise me something...
Swear you won't flip up Haru'ue's
skirt, even as a joke, okay?
Huh? But why would I do something like that?
Well, uh...
you...
you know...
All right...! Where should we go now?
Your choice...
Anything special you want to do?
Oh, well, um...
I don't know this district well enough to say.
Oh... of course.
Hey... I know!
This spot's becoming the place where friendships begin!
It is, huh...?
This is where we came when I first met you and Uiharu.
It's good?
You've got a little bit on your face, though.
Still... it's too bad the others couldn't come...
Why would Judgment and Antiskill be holding a
joint conference about something like earthquakes?
It'd make more sense if it was a case.
Heh, heh... I didn't really want to get into it earlier...
but there's a hot rumor going around about that.
There is one thing we know for certain
about the recent spate of tremors in the city.
Despite what many people think...
they are not earthquakes.
To be precise...
Poltergeists? You're kidding me.
No! I really think this is true!
What are we talking about here?
Furniture moving around on its own, and stuff?
No P-waves or S-waves were observed!
It's a paranormal phenomenon,
I'm telling you! Paranormal!
No doubt the rumor mill is already
churning with all sorts of absurd ideas,
so let me make this perfectly clear.
This is not a paranormal phenomenon.
The cause of poltergeisting is simultaneous,
multiple incidents of RSPK Syndrome.
What does she mean? What is RSPK Syndrome?
We're about to find out.
At this point, I am going to turn the floor over to
Miss Terrestina of the Multi-Active
Rescue Team, who'll explain further.
Hello! As Miss Yomikawa has informed you.
My name is Terrestina and I am
with the Multi-Active Rescue Team
RSPK Syndrome refers to the state or phenomenon that
occurs when an Esper temporarily loses their autonomy,
causing their abilities to
unconsciously run out of control.
The phenomenon varies according to the Esper.
Please look at the display if you will.
When these phenomena occur simultaneously,
the runaway abilities can merge with each other,
and manifest as a uniform poltergeist phenomenon.
As the poltergeisting gains in
strength and spreads over a wide area,
the resulting occurrence can be virtually
indistinguishable from the effects of an earthquake.
The recent tremors we've experienced
are the result of this poltergeisting.
We're still investigating the cause of the
multiple RSPK Syndrome incidents that are responsible.
Unfortunately, there are sure to be a few students
who will believe this is some sort of occult power.
It's a pulse from an alternate dimension!
Or another planet!
Oh! Or maybe the result of secret underground
experiments conducted by the government!
In any case...
Belief in such nonsense could lead to mass hysteria...
which would only increase the number of casualties.
That is why we have asked
Judgment to attend this conference...
We want you to take measures to ensure that
students are not spreading inflammatory rumors.
Try to put a stop to them before they start.
They say we can expect a really
big one to happen before much longer.
You see?
Oh, yeah, you're from District Nineteen, right, Haru'ue?
Weren't there several
poltergeisting outbreaks in that area?
What was it like?
Hey, you shouldn't be getting so
excited about this kind of thing.
It could be really serious.
Well, that was over a lot sooner than I expected.
It says that Antiskill has an
additional meeting after the joint one.
You look like you have something on your mind, Konori.
Those RSPK Syndrome incidents she was describing...
I've never heard of them...
And the way they're handling this...
something about it just doesn't sit right with me.
Why? They have specialists investigating the occurrences.
That's their job, after all...
At any rate, it's not gonna do any
good for us to try and figure it all out.
You're probably right, but even so...
Hey! We're done here!
Where are you guys now?
All right, Haru'ue.
What game would you like to try out next?
Oh...! I know, over here!
Uiharu sure is in rare form, huh?
It looks like you are, too, Sissy
Oh, no... No, these are...
You know, something about those
coins looks familiar to me...
Oh... You're playing whack-a-mole?
Yeah... Well, sort of anyway.
I played that when I was younger.
It's so fun.
I've never seen anything like it before.
Look at them popping up like that. So cute!
Yes... very cute...
But, you know...
You might try hitting them, instead of just staring.
Hit the moles?
But that's cruel.
Oh... I guess you're right.
Uh... okay!
You can play the game any way you want to.
One more time.
Um... that'll be the fourth time in a row...
Hey... you guys, why don't we check that out?
What is it?
Say "cheese!"
Cheese!
Let's see...
Sending...
There we go!
Here.
How should I put this?
The girl is a curiosity.
Really? She seems sweet.
Actually, she reminds me of how Uiharu used to be.
What do you mean?
You know... back when she'd first transferred in.
Where are you going?
Look out!
Oh, dear... You ran right into it.
You okay?
Up there.
That poster?
The one for the fireworks show?
Oh... yeah, that's supposed to be tonight, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Hey, we should all go together.
That's a great idea!
We can dress up and everything!
Well, what do you say?
This is gonna be great!
Yeah!
I never worn one of these. It feels strange.
Me too, I know what you mean.
Isn't it a little long?
I'm looking up how to wear them.
Oh, here, I think I found something!
Use the sash to adjust the length...
Sounds easy enough.
It looks pretty complicated.
Well... we can give it a try!
Let's see here...
First, we pair up the front, like so...
Ah... What a beautiful pendant!
It's special...
It's kind of a good luck charm.
A good luck charm, huh?
How nice.
Now... let's see if we can get this to fit right.
Okay... so what's the next step in the process?
"After you pair up the front, you should raise the
garment's collar approximately twenty centimeters..."
I wanted to thank you.
Huh?
I mean it...
You've helped me so much...
I can tell that you're a good person.
Oh... it's nothing...
As a Judgment officer, I'm happy to help you...
Really, I'm having a lot more fun with
this than with my other duties lately...
Sweeping up, looking for stuff people have lost...
Oh, I see.
Anyway... I'm happy to do anything
I can to help you feel at home...
So... you can always count on me!
Oh... I'm starting to understand why
you needed me to come over so urgently.
Don't just stand there!
Help us out of this thing!
There!
That should do it.
It's perfect. Thank you.
That was amazing, Saten...
You made it look perfect in no time at all!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
We're gonna be late. Let's hurry up.
I made a mess of things.
If I'd known how good you were at
this, I would've asked before we started.
Come on now, you're doing just fine.
Well, I figure it should be my turn to help out this time.
How so?
Do you remember how difficult it was
for me to pass all those Judgment tests...
and how that, in turn, made me
insecure about other stuff, too?
Yeah, I do...
You were in quite a state, huh?
Constantly getting down on yourself.
But fortunately, I didn't have to do it all alone.
You kept encouraging me.
You and the others were there for me when I needed help.
Oh, yeah? And we were helpful?
Yes.
It was all thanks to you guys.
I finally passed the tests...!
And that's why...
I think it's my turn now... to help
Haru'ue the same way that you guys helped me.
Oh... I mean...
it's not that I'm the only one you should turn to...
I'm really glad that I have you for a roommate, Uiharu.
I trust you!
Oh... good!
Look at you...!
Being recognized for your good deeds at last...
I am so proud!
Geez! You make it sound as though
I'm a little kid or something.
My kid sister!
I'm older than you!
Now, stop fidgeting.
We need to get you dressed, don't we?
Ready? Let's go.
Whew!
Surely we're safe after that, don't you think?
Escape successful!
We're on our way!
Could our dorm be any more of a drag?
They won't even change our curfew for a fireworks show?
Quit fidgeting. Your outfit will be
down around your ankles if you continue.
Yeah, okay.
Although... I guess it doesn't really matter,
since you're still wearing those stupid shorts under it.
What's the big deal?
Nobody is gonna see them.
I don't have to see them, but that doesn't change the fact
that I know you have them on.
Anyway... Is Konori coming with us tonight?
Well, she said she wanted to start
investigating these poltergeisting incidents...
Something's been nagging at her ever
since the conference this afternoon.
Hmm... You have to admit, it is weird...
All these events occurring, almost
as if they've been coordinated.
Man, this is taking me forever.
I don't know if the net's ever
seemed more full of useless information.
Wow! Misaka, you look fantastic!
You, too, Shirai. You're both adorable!
Would you expect any less?
And you guys look wonderful, as well.
Uh... thank you... We did try.
Ah! All those stands!
You're right!
There sure are a lot.
Mmm, it smells so good!
I'm going!
Me too!
Sissy, be careful running down that hill!
What do you think?
Should we go?
Yes, please!
Come on, Sissy. You look ridiculous.
Hey,... What's the big deal?
It's a festival, right?
I'm just getting into the spirit.
Honestly!
Huh? What are those trucks for?
MAR. They're with the Multi Active Rescue Team.
They must be a countermeasure for all the poltergeisting.
Poltergeisting?!
Then... all the rumors are true?
It would be a real mess if one of those
incidents happened here with all these people around.
It's not that I don't get why they're here...
but it's a shame on a night like tonight...
They don't exactly blend in at a festival.
Oh...! Just a second.
I know the perfect place to go!
Nice, huh? We've got a great view here.
Hey, look, you guys!
There's another round going.
You can kind of feel the "boom" in your tummy, can't you?
Yeah...
Like... like an echo.
It's so pretty.
Maybe I should have gone to the festival.
It still feels like something's wrong.
But I'm not making any headway.
What's this?
AIM diffusion fields?
What a great show!
Woo... hoo!
Here they come!
Light up the sky!!
Is something the matter?
I was just remembering.
Remembering what?
More like "who".
You see... I had a friend once...
We were super close, just like the two of you are.
Are you okay?
Something wrong?
Where's she going?
Haru'ue!
Hold on a sec!
Huh? I wonder where they're going.
Finally! They're taking the hint
and giving us time alone together!
Now we can imitate the fireworks and
let our bodies glow with passionate fire!
Let go! I don't feel like fighting you.
It's too hot out here!
As hot as the flame that burns in my heart for you!
Huh? Who could it be?
Hi, Konori. What are you doing, calling me at this hour?
Listen! It's about the poltergeist incidents!
I know that doing research is important, but
would it hurt you to take a breather once in a while?
The fireworks show is beautiful.
Just listen to me, will you?!
I've found a possible cause
for the RSPK Syndrome activity.
Intentional outside interference
with AIM diffusion fields.
AIM diffusion fields.
So, what are you saying?
That all of this poltergeisting
lately isn't just some random accident!
Where are you?
Where have you gone?
Haru'ue... what's wrong?
Where are you?
You're saying there's actually
somebody orchestrating these events?
What was that?
Shirai, hello?
Is this?!
I think so.
It's poltergeisting!
I've got you!
What about the other three?
Uiharu!
Saten, are you all right?
That was a close call.
Are you injured...?
You're safe now.
I know that lady!
Haru'ue! Can you hear me?
Good, you're awake...
Are you okay?
That was quite a fall.
Where?
Where are you?
Please, where?
I don't understand.
Wow, that's amazing!
Something's collapsed.
Was there an accident?
Where are you?
Where did you go?
This direction, Haru'ue...
No! No! Not that way! Over here!
It's the blind leading the blind.