That was an odd noise.
What was that? A firecracker?
It startled me.
Yeah.
There was another incident?
Yes, it was the fifth one so far.
Luckily the explosion was
relatively small, and no one was hurt.
Even so...
Even so, if it's just a prank, it's not a very funny one.
So, have any leads so far?
Well, it's not much, but we finally
got something to go on yesterday.
Tell me, Sissy, do you know about gravitons at all?
Gravitons.
Um, those are gravity particles, right?
Yes, that's right.
In each of the attacks, the satellite
detected a sharp spike in gravitons
immediately before the explosion occurred.
The speed of the gravitons was accelerated
explosively using an aluminum base,
so they popped out into the surrounding area.
Thus, the aluminum was transformed into a bomb
as far as we can tell.
Hm.
Why use aluminum, though?
Who knows?
Well, shouldn't you?
Anyway, at least this indicates it
was the work of an Esper, doesn't it?
Just search through Academy City's
databank, and you should have the guy.
The data bank registers all of the students' ability info.
Of course. That was the first place we turned to.
The corresponding ability is called Synchrotron.
We found only one Esper whose power
could be used to make aluminum explode.
It was a Level 4 student.
That's simple. This person must be the suspect.
Except the thing is, she has an alibi.
It's solid, too.
The girl has been in the hospital.
So, there's no way she could have
orchestrated any of the attacks.
So, that's ruled out.
The inquiry's reached a dead-end, then?
I'd say so.
I can't believe there would be
such an oversight in the databank.
Oh. Well, maybe...
Maybe there's an unregistered Esper out there
or something.
Hm...
So,
I think I should join in on the search for this criminal.
No, absolutely not.
I know how you think.
Let's see.
"This could be fun, facing a new opponent.
Yes, I'd like the chance to pit my powers against his.
That's exactly what you were just thinking, wasn't it?
Don't lie.
No. I would never think that.
Don't you know that you can't fool me?
I can see right through you.
Come on, now.
It's like I've told you over and over.
Remember that you're a civilian, Sissy,
and maintaining the peace of the city...
It is a job for Judgment or Antiskill, and nobody else."
I know.
You've told me that enough.
If you think I serve in Judgment
because I get a kick out of this sort of thing,
you're sadly mistaken.
Now, look. That's not what I was saying!
Listen to me.
I need you to make some promises now.
First one, that you will not go recklessly
poking your nose into this case.
Is this really necessary?
I don't think that you're...
And second, in the unlikely
event that you do become involved,
you will not charge into a fight,
but wait for Judgment to arrive on the scene.
Hey, now.
I always take care of things before you guys show...
And third, you must not wear shorts under your skirt.
What's that got to do with anything?
It may not deal directly with this issue,
but I wanted to use this opportunity
to help you elevate your sense of style.
You must remember, Sissy,
that as the Ace of Tokiwadai,
you have an image to uphold.
You still seem to
lack the self awareness necessary to be...
This is totally off-topic!
No. Please listen to me.
If you were more self-aware,
you would realize that the Ace should not sleep
with a teddy bear nor bathe with a strange frog doll.
It's about time for you
to let go of those childish things.
And there's more.
For instance, those cutesy pajamas you insist on wearing.
I mean, you are the third ranked Level 5 Esper...
Who do you think you are?
Why should I ever listen to you?
Oh. I see.
Well, what do you think?
Uh, well, maybe...
Could you sit down, if that's okay?
I think it'll help.
Here's my theory.
I think Shirai means well and her concern
is keeping you safe and out of danger.
Out of danger?
Like with these graviton attacks we've had.
Oh. Is that their formal name now?
At first, they were just put into empty tin
cans or garbage bins, but the suspect has evolved.
The latest bombs were put into stuffed animals
or other toys to make them less suspicious.
Who would do that? It's awful.
You can see how serious it is now
and why Shirai might be a bit concerned about you helping.
Thank you for waiting.
One fruit parfait, as ordered.
Wow! Finally!
I am so hungry!
U... i... ha... ru!
Oh! Hello, Shirai.
Trying to duck your responsibility
by lounging around here?
Well? Are you ready to go on patrol?
Of course.
Oh! But, uh, my parfait.
Uh... Aw, just a bite? Please don't...
I asked Uiharu to join me here to have a snack.
Hm?
If that's a problem, then you should talk to me.
It's nothing to do with you.
This is exclusively a Judgment matter.
So, we civilians should butt out, is that it?
What more do you want from me, Sissy?
Like I've already explained,
whatever you want to imagine,
Judgment work isn't exactly a walk in the park.
Wha...?
Ah, my parfait! Please, just one bite!
She is so condescending!
All I hear is "Judgment this" and "Judgment that."
I'd be more impressed by them if they
showed up before I'd taken care of everything.
Well, whatever.
I'll give it to her later.
What are you just standing around for?
Uh, sorry.
You mean me?
Do I have it wrong? Are you not my backup?
Your backup? What?
Oh! No.
You see, funny story, one of my friends just left this...
Stop blabbering and put on your armband.
We need to go! Come with me.
What? Where are we going?
To do our jobs, obviously.
Oh. Have you not heard yet?
To do our jobs? That means I...
Hey. You don't know what's going on, do you?
Come to think of it, I don't know your face.
Are you one of the new recruits?
Hm...
Yes! I'm Misaka,
and this is my first day!
Misaka.
You know, I think I've heard that somewhere before.
I'm sorry, but I don't know your name.
I'm Mii Konori of the 177th Branch.
Good afternoon, Konori.
Nice to meet you!
Oh. Yes. Same to you.
I'll show her that a civilian is
perfectly capable of doing Judgment work.
They can throw whatever they want at me.
I'll take it!
Here.
What is that thing?
What is this? It's a broom, obviously.
Oh.
We're here to tidy this place up.
Uh, really?
It's just, well, you know.
I'm in Judgment and all.
Exactly. Students throw their litter about,
and we in Judgment have to pick up after them.
Didn't you learn that in your training?
Eh... Oh!
Yes, I remember that now!
This is what Judgment does?
You've got to be kidding me.
Hey, you just threw trash on the ground!
Oh. You can get this, too.
You little punk! Come back here, right now!
Huh. You got what you deserved.
Now throw...
Eh... Huh? Uh...
Seriously?
I can't believe anybody would be
careless enough to leave their armband here.
Well, what did they say?
No luck.
No one saw anything matching its
description, and nothing's been turned in.
I'm sorry.
What am I going to do with you?
You'll have to submit an official report.
But, for now, let's go back to the branch office a...
What's the matter?
Are you lost, sweetie?
What were you thinking?
You can't get trigger-happy with your powers.
Yeah, but...
"But" nothing Misaka.
The use of your ability is one thing.
Guarding the safety of the city is another.
Uh... Oh, yeah.
I think I remember now.
That was part of my training.
Before you look to your training,
look to your common sense.
The work of Judgment isn't exactly a walk in the park!
Come on.
I'll do better!
I promise you I can do this job!
Yes, of course.
Just hang in there.
It's no use. I should quit.
Oh, thank you.
Being out in the field is a lot
different than training, isn't it?
Yeah. Totally.
I guess I never realized how difficult it
could be to give directions and help people.
Yeah. It was hard for me, too.
You know, the maps.
It can be a hassle even when you think you know the place.
Yes. Konori here.
Right.
I hear you.
We'll both keep our eyes open for it, then.
Well, it looks like we've got something to find.
Oh yeah, really?
Yeah. They say it's a bag.
A bag?
In the beginning it was just garbage bins,
but the latest bombs were put into stuffed animals
or other toys to make them less suspicious.
The bag we want, could it be a kid's by any chance?
Well, yeah, but how did you know that?
Apparently it's pink and has some flowers on it.
She said she left it on a bench,
and then a dog grabbed it and started running away.
No! Not a dog!
We have to do something now!
Come on. Let's hurry up and go catch it.
Well, yeah.
It would be a pain if he dropped it somewhere.
You're worried about that?
We would have no way of telling who walked away with it.
So...
It could be anywhere.
Let's go!
We need to find that bag!
Uh... Uh... huh.
Of course.
Hey, sorry.
But I can't really squeeze through there.
Don't worry about it.
I'm almost all the way through. I think.
Are you okay, Misaka?
There's a bug.
It has lots of legs.
Ah! No! Get away!
Come on. Where are you hiding?
What is it?
There's a bug. It has no legs!
Ah! No! Get away!
Hm.
No, nothing here.
Why do I have to be on the bottom?
And what is she doing?
The bag we're looking for isn't gonna be up there.
This is stupid!
A little bit more to the right, please.
Yeah. Sure.
Ah! There's a bug!
Ah! Whoa. Steady, now.
Oh, really? Area D, as well?
Okay, thank you.
We appreciate all your help with this matter.
Oh, hey. Is Uiharu here?
Yeah, she's in the back.
Yes. Judgment. Branch 177.
There you are!
You gotta listen to this.
I finally found the song I was looking for.
Shh!
She's finally tired enough to sleep.
Aw, she's adorable!
I never knew you had a little girl.
Yeah! No. Wait.
So, when will she get flowers?
You know these don't grow out of my head, right?
Oh, I see.
And for your information,
I don't have any children, either.
But look at her.
Right around the eyes. Do you see?
Not my daughter!
Easy, now.
You'll wake her up if you're not careful.
You're the one being loud, Saten.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
So, who is she?
Did she get lost or something?
It's not that.
We're just trying to help find her bag for her,
that's all.
Apparently it was a birthday present from her parents,
so it's very important.
So we've asked the other branches
to assist us in the search, also.
Until the search is complete,
Shirai and I are looking after her.
Wow. All of Judgment looking for a bag?
Why is it such a big deal?
Life is much different here.
You're completely separated from your family.
It's something everybody
understands when a child is homesick.
Hm. Judgment handles more than I ever realized before now.
There, there.
It really matters.
I'm sick of this. Where are you?
Hey! Watch where you're going, punk.
You bump into someone without apologizing?
No. I didn't.
You ran...
Aw, look. The little twerp wants to argue!
Stop it! What are you doing?
It's Judgment. So no big deal, then.
What do you mean, "No big deal then"?
You two were just ganging up on that guy.
Shut up already.
What a brat.
No. Patience. Patience.
Are you okay?
It's a little late for that.
That wasn't very polite.
Hey, Misaka.
Well? Did you find it?
Oh! No.
Not here either, huh?
Where haven't we looked for it yet? Let's see.
Maybe here.
No. Please don't tell me it's in the park.
There are all these kids here.
True. Children and dogs don't always get along.
Dogs? That's not what I'm talking about!
Really?
Because it's a dog we're looking for.
No, I... I mean, are you sure?
Let's concentrate on the bag.
Why don't you start over there, okay?
Hey! Don't leave me!
Off you go, now.
That's not fair.
Hey, lady, are you a Judgment officer?
That's a Tokiwadai uniform!
Are you a princess?
Uh, I...
She's wearing shorts underneath her skirt. Look!
Why do you think she's wearing those?
Maybe it's a princess thing.
Hey. Don't you have underwear like normal people?
I'm wearing them underneath the shorts!
She's going commando!
A commando Judgment officer!
You don't know what you're talking about!
Ooh, look. A dog!
Got you!
Konori, quick!
Stop right there!
I can take care of this.
He's fast! I don't have any choice.
Hah... hah! I've got you!
Huh?
Look out!
No!
It's mine now!
Misaka!
Target safely recovered.
She's so cool!
She is a princess!
I knew it.
Well done, Misaka. That was something.
Whoa!
Uh, don't you think you should handle it more gently?
And shouldn't we be calling in the bomb squad now?
Uh,
what are you talking about?
Here. Try not to lose it again.
Yeah!
That was really good work.
I knew Konori would come through!
I'm not the one who found it, actually.
What was Misaka doing here?
I'm sorry. I didn't realize
you were acquainted with Misaka.
Um, acquainted with her?
That's Mikoto Misaka.
You know, from Tokiwadai?
Mikoto. Misaka.
You don't mean the Railgun?
Well, yeah. But what is she doing here?
And, more importantly, what is she doing soaking wet?
Oh, about that.
She actually dove into the fountain
to protect the bag from going in.
Apparently she was convinced that
there was a bomb inside the bag.
Hey, is that my...
Seriously, how does this happen
after all the lectures I've given her?
Hey, now. This is totally something she would do.
K... Kuroko!
I, uh, I can explain.
There's no need to be flustered.
Miss Railgun of Tokiwadai.
Oh. Uh, well...
She knows, then?
Okay, that's cool.
Come on. This way.
Pretty lady.
Thanks a lot!
Oh.
I mean, really I just...
You're very welcome!
Good job, sweetie.
Mm... hm!
After everything I said, Sissy,
Job well done.
This has been one heck of a day, hasn't it?
You'll get no sympathy from me.
You're the one who decided to play Judgment officer
because you were annoyed with the rules
I'd laid out for you.
I hope you learned your lesson this time, at least.
It sure is hard, huh?
Being in Judgment, I mean.
What are you saying?
Maybe I should look at you in a different light.
You don't know how much I have
longed for this day to come.
Please look at me in a different light!
If this one doesn't work,
I'm happy to change it for you, Sissy!
Whoa! No! I didn't mean that literally!
Sissy!
Sissy! Just look at me! I'll change the light!
Anything you want! Oh, Sissy!
Keep it down!
We're with Judgment!
I need everybody to evacuate the store at once!
Hey, what's going on?
What's happening in my store?
Sir, we have detected accelerated gravitons here.
You what?
I'm sorry, but it's possible there's a bomb
hidden somewhere in this store.
Wha? A bomb?
Damn. Where is it?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I fell.
Let's get you out of here.
Thank you.
No! Not yet!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
He shielded me.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
I said I was gonna do it, and I'm doing it now!
Doing what? Who are you?