A Level Six Esper?
Yes.
That's what you will become, dear.
You will be the very embodiment
of Academy City's greatest dream.
Oh, Grandfather!
How amazing! Will that really happen?
Yes.
Today... we lay the groundwork... dear.
Yellow Marble leader reporting in, ma'am.
We have arrived.
Now commencing installation.
Brown Marble leader, how are you coming along.?
Is the blue car following you?
Right on schedule.
Then it's time to put an end to these foolish dreams.
I'm tired of waiting.
Let's move right to the finale.
Just you wait.
When I get my hands on you...
What was that?
Come on...
Is this really your idea of fun?
Just a fancy little trick I wanted to try.
What are you doing?
Why the hell did you choose now to interfere?
Well, say something!
Dr. Kiyama!
Those trucks are only decoys!
The children aren't inside them!
They're not there? But...
Come on, Saten, hurry.
Hey wait, calm down, I'm going.
What do you two girls think you're doing?
Watch it. You're squishing me!
Just sit still!
I'm going to be your navigator.
Now, get in!
You want to save the children, right?
Okay, get ready, Sissy!
If you guys wanna fight, I'm happy to play along.
Helicopter, huh?
I think you're about done here.
Ugh. I recognize that ability all too well.
I think you can relax, ladies.
The cavalry is here.
Try not to be too intimidated by my ability.
"Aero Hand" will make swift work of our opponents.
That was good timing!
Go on. We can take care of things from here.
You go catch up with Kiyama and the others, Sissy.
Kuroko.
All right, then.
But you had better catch up.
Or you'll answer to me!
Who would dare to assault me?
I am Kuroko Shirai of Tokiwadai,
partner of the great Railgun!
Hold on! That phrase sounds suspiciously familiar...
Konori! On it!
We're ready now.
Let's do this!
I have to say...
This is rather unexpected...
I never thought we would team up for a fight.
We can use this opportunity to settle something:
"Whose ability is the greater one"?
Shortly after the other squad moved out, Antiskill
surveillance picked up something interesting.
They recorded two transport vehicles posing
as civilian trucks departing MAR headquarters.
Most likely...
Those are the real transports.
I can't believe I fell hook, line, and
sinker for that madwoman's amateur trick.
We need to hurry...
It looks like the transport has
already reached its destination.
Where is it?
An unused propulsion system
laboratory in School District 23.
Take this exit on the left.
Oh... Good work, Doctor...
Of course, I wouldn't expect
anything less from an opponent like you.
Hold on tight!
That's what will make killing you. Such an amusing task!
Hold on, Konori. I've got this!
Hey... what made that thunk just now?
Come on, come on!
I want to see you run like your life depends on it.
Which, of course, it does.
Better keep moving!
I know that voice.
So do I. That evil witch.
Hey... That's Misaka.
Uh... what are you doing out there?
Quick, you need to go faster!
Yes, I kind of noticed that.
I'm sorry.
About before...
I was wrong, I know that.
I suppose I can't really blame you.
In your position, I would have done the same thing.
I'll make up for my failure.
I'll beat her...
I will!
My attacks were deflected!
Did you really think your little
shocks would work against me?
All right, then.
Take this!
I know about that trick, too.
Impossible!
I've done my homework, you see.
I'm up to date on everything they have in
the databank concerning that ability of yours.
Including the especially interesting fact
that your railgun's range is only fifty meters.
I'm getting sick of this woman.
Take the next turnoff on the left.
What's that?
I missed...
Oh, well.
The targets are headed your way now, Green Marble.
Crush them.
We're under attack!
Take care of it!
There's no way you're getting past
us, so you shouldn't bother trying!
Yes, that's right.
We've managed to gain control of
all ramps from this point forward.
Sorry, but we're being harried from above, too.
This is the most we can do for you right now.
Why is Antiskill helping me?
Never mind that.
Just hurry up and get to those children!
Why am I surrounded by incompetents?
Very well. I'll take care of it myself.
Huh? Again?
Hold on tight up there!
It's a lost cause.
Give up, already! You don't stand a chance!
It doesn't matter how hard you try or how fast you run.
You might as well pack up and go home.
You're never gonna be able to save those brats.
I'll make sure of it!
I won't stop.
I swore that I would revive them!
I have to try!
A teacher doesn't give up on her
students just because things get tough!
I would never expect you to.
No matter what happens, I'll make certain you get to them.
That's why I'm here.
And I promise you, I'm not gonna give up, either!
Little fools.
You don't have any cards left to play now.
Just roll over and die!
Misaka!
Ha! Another pathetic attempt!
I know all of your attacks, remember?
Nothing you can do will surprise me!
Oh, really?
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Kuroko!
On my way!
Yes, I can fire coins.
But that isn't all.
I'll show you the full extent of my power!
What the...
How rude.
Teleporting away without warning like that.
Shirai, Misaka!
You guys terrified us...! Are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine. Don't worry.
You saved us.
I want to...
Hold on.
Don't say it...
Let's wait until after we've saved the children.
Right.
Well?
Can you figure it out?
Almost there.
The security on this is pretty tight.
How annoying.
This would be a lot easier if you
hadn't taken out every single one of them.
Oh, yeah? How was I supposed to know?
I figured they would have left at
least one person inside to guard it.
Got it!
In this facility, there's only one area
where power consumption is especially high.
The lowermost block.
I found you!
Haru'ue! Can you hear me?
Wake up!
We came for you! All right...
where's the control panel for this?
Hold on... I'll go look over there.
Great, thank you!
Not long now.
We'll get you out of there.
What is it...? What's the matter?
No, that sound again!
It can't be.
But it is.
You pesky, meddling brats.
Oh, no.
It's her!
This is to pay you back for earlier!
Shirai, Misaka! You okay?
How dare you?!
What was that?
Ah... that felt good.
You think you can get away
with making me look like a fool?
Her again!
You're using Capacity Down!
Misaka described it to us before...
The sound it emits only affects Espers!
This is Capacity Down?
What's your point?
Knowing what it does isn't going to protect you from it.
She told us that you'd upgraded it, though.
That the speakers were a lot bigger than they were before.
Too big to be moved easily.
That's right.
It wasn't easy to do, but I've
placed them throughout the facility.
Would you care to go around destroying them one by one?
It still has to have a control center.
And its size limits where that could be.
I know a little about this building's structure.
From what I can tell...
the power center must be back where we just were.
The central control room!
Uiharu...
You might be right.
But what does that matter?
There's nothing you can do about it now.
Ugh. Do all little girls talk as much as you?
You should thank me.
I'm about to show you something amazing.
The culmination of years of research.
The completion of the ability crystal.
How can you?
I don't understand.
You're a victim in this, too.
Your own grandfather used you for his experiments.
He made your ability run out of control.
And yet here you are.
You're wrong.
I'm no victim.
I'm Academy City's ultimate dream.
This seed of greatness was born thanks to me.
And I intend to let it bloom.
It can't be. That vial.
It contains the First Sample?
Using this, I am finally going to create a Level 6.
Hah!
A Level 6?
No way.
Oh, yes.
This young girl is about to become the
first esper in Academy City to reach Level 6.
The power of the other children will flow into her!
You can't do it!
Not Haru'ue!
Under specific wavelengths, she has
a reception ability above her level.
It was truly a stroke of luck to find someone whose
ability can resonate with the crystal like hers can.
High-level Telepaths are quite rare, after all.
Why them?
Why use these same children again?
Why are they always the ones who have to suffer the most?
It's not so bad.
They probably won't even feel a thing.
I'm just going to borrow the realities
they've created inside their minds.
You're talking about Personal Reality.
You can call it whatever you want.
Shall I explain the process to you?
Essentially, I'm extracting the neurotransmitters
that control activity within the brain.
Particularly those which make them runaway
Espers and fusing them with the First Sample.
By doing so, I will create an
inhibitor for the ability crystal.
And it will be perfected at last.
The old geezer never could figure it out.
He spent all his time applying minor
changes that were ultimately useless.
And now... only one step left.
Don't do it!
Why not?
Do you realize what will happen?
If you do this, and the children
awaken while still in their runaway state.
Then Academy City will be hit by an unprecedented
wave of poltergeisting, and it will be destroyed.
So what? That's fine by me.
"Someone who attains the power of God
while still inhabiting a mortal body."
Creating such a person is the whole point of this city!
And once that's done, there's no real reason
for Academy City to remain standing anymore.
Careful.
You're going to get yourself hurt.
Dr. Kiyam...
Just lay there and be quiet like a good little girl.
Please, Saten!
Please hurry!
Come on!
Where is it?
I have to find that Capacity Down thingy!
You said something interesting before.
I can hear her.
That Skill Out members weren't my lab rats.
Well, you were just one word away from being correct.
They aren't my only lab rats.
No, you are all my lab rats, don't you see?
Would you prefer a different analogy? Very well.
Academy City is my breeding farm,
and all you children are my livestock.
Misaka... hang on...
I think it's time to put you down, though.
What the?
What was that?
I don't give a damn if you think we're lab rats.
Don't forget.
Rats have sharp teeth!
That sounds like.
Thank goodness! Saten!
There's another one of you brats here?
How is she still standing?
I'm not going to tell you twice.
Keep your hands off my friends!
It went away!
Damn it!
Fine, then.
Looks like it's time to change tactics.
Fortunately, I have a plan B.
I'm going to blow you and this whole place away!
I built this particular weapon
after carefully analyzing your ability.
It's even more powerful than your railgun.
Honestly, first laboratory rats, then livestock.
How bitter and pathetic do you have to
be to think so lowly of other human beings?
You may be a Level 5 Electromaster.
In this town, however, you're
nothing more than a bunch of data.
That's right! Just a bunch of
data with two legs and a smart mouth!
That's where you've got it all wrong.
The people of Academy City are so much more than that.
Anything is possible in this place.
Here we can achieve greatness.
In a way that we couldn't anywhere else.
So you see.
You think you're human beings?
You're just samples.
That's what Academy City was made for!
I'll stop you... for the sake of my city!
That was nice work.
You saved all our lives, Saten.
Is that it?
Yes.
The program is complete.
And now.
Go on, it's all right.
Banri spoke to me.
She wanted me to tell you.
"I trust you, teacher."
Teacher?
You look tired...
Why do you have those dark circles under your eyes?
I... I've just been very busy.
There was so much work to do.
Oh, yeah.
And you know what?
Your hair's longer.
It's her, though.
That's our teacher.
It's Miss Kiyama.
She's here!
My children are all awake.
Hey, Erii.
I want to thank you...
for hearing my voice.
You're a true friend.
Yeah!
All right...
can I finish saying it now?
Thank you so much.
How can I describe it best?
A battle of singular heroism!
Of course, it didn't take long for
Shirai to lose her nerve and run away...
but I wasn't about to let that stop me.
I stood firm, facing the enemy
head-on, defeating them easily.
Wow! Then you were the one who finally put an end
to all the dreadful poltergeisting that was happening?
Oh, was it really you, Kongo?
We should have known!
When is it coming?
Any moment now.
Aw, man, I can't wait!
So, where are they?
Uiharu and the others.
She said they would be along in just
a minute and we should go on ahead.
They're running later than I thought, though.
I hope they make it.
This is a special day.
We have to hurry! I don't want to miss it!
Misaka, Shirai, it's unlike you to be late.
What's gotten into you?
Honestly! Of all days, Sissy, this
is the one you choose to sleep in on?
Shut up!
You were sleeping every bit as soundly as I was!
I have to admit, I'm kinda surprised.
I would never have expected Misaka
to come up with something like this.
What are you talking about?
It's sweet and generous and
thoughtful, just like Misaka is.
Yeah...
I don't think I'd go that far.
Hello, Shirai?
Oh? You haven't gotten there yet?
No, I don't need anything from you guys right now.
Just calling to let you know that
you-know-who's regained consciousness.
We've begun interrogating her, but I don't
think she's going to give much up easily.
Yeah, I agree.
All right.
Thanks for letting me know.
What is it?
It's going to be a long time before we
have a full account of Therestina's crimes.
Hey! What are we doing standing around?
We need to hurry!
Look...! Up there!
Hey, it's here!
Look, there it is!
Where?
Look!
That's so cool!
Okay. One, two, three...
Ready, go!
We just wanted to say...
Happy birthday Miss Kiyama!
Rest up and get well soon, okay?
We'll do the same!
I can't wait to see you again!
Me, neither!
Bye for now, Teacher...
Thank you so much!
We love you!
There's never a dull moment, is there?
Not in this city.