Hello there, Haru'ue.
Your friends are here.
You said my friends were here.
You mean Uiharu and the others?
Well, why don't we just see?
It's... Banri?
Yes! It is you!
Incredible!
You're here. I can't believe it!
I need to tell Uiharu about this right away!
So, the ten child subjects who've been missing
are now securely installed at MAR's laboratory?
Yes.
They've been found, finally.
Isn't that great, Uiharu?
Oh... yeah.
And the woman responsible for the Level
Upper incident is behind this situation as well.
She said that she didn't care if the city was
destroyed, so long as the children were saved?
That's a pretty extreme stance, wouldn't you say?
So, Therestina said she's going to find
a way to wake up Edasaki and the others?
Huh?
Oh... yeah.
Well, then, it sounds like we've closed the case.
Excellent work!
Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
I know you all too well, Sissy.
I'm guessing you're still
concerned about Kiyama, aren't you?
You still aren't convinced it was the right idea
to have the children taken away from her, right?
I'm just not sure.
Well, be sure.
You made the right choice.
At least that's what I believe, anyway.
Right.
Even so.
You crossed the line this time, Sissy!
Going into a place like that on your own?
If anything had happened to you, I
don't know what I would have done!
Hello, there.
You're spacing out now. Are you okay?
Oh... yeah.
Come on. Aren't you anxious to see how Haru'ue's doing?
Well.. Yeah... I guess.
She'll be thrilled to see you!
Let's get a move on!
Hey! All this pushing isn't really necessary!
Now, now, you don't want to keep her waiting, do you?
Let go!
Thrilled to see me, huh?
Well... maybe I should bring her some things.
Let's see here...
Snacks, a game, some reading material...
And what else?
Changes of clothing, of course!
Waiting isn't good enough anymore.
I need to start looking for her.
Oh, Haru'ue.
I'm so proud of you.
I would do anything to save them.
anything in the entire world!
The whole city can hate and revile me. I don't
care! I'm not going to let anything stop me now!
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I don't have anything yet.
I... um...
Oh, it's you.
I have this friend, Haru'ue.
Maybe you've already heard of her by now.
I actually haven't known her for very long.
But she did tell me that she and Banri
Edasaki were friends when they were little.
And.. you see...
Haru'ue is a telepath.
Every time one of the poltergeisting incidents
occurred, she could hear Edasaki's voice.
Because of the way she acted, she
was suspected of being responsible.
Even so, she did everything she could
to hear what Edasaki was saying to her.
But now Edasaki isn't missing anymore...
so...
Surely...
Surely, Haru'ue must be happy
with the way things have turned out.
So, what are you trying to say?
I don't really know.
I just thought I should tell you.
I was so close to finishing the
vaccine that would help them...
All I needed was to get my hands on the First Sample.
I could have gotten their runaway abilities under control.
I could have awakened them at last.
I could have brought them back!
Dr. Kiyama.
Let's collect all of your data and take it to MAR.
It's bound to be of some use.
And then they'd let us in to see Edasaki and the others.
I couldn't possibly.
I know that's what you want.
Let's go see them!
How can I say no to that?
Wow, you came all the way out
here to bring me your research?
That's right.
Although... we were also hoping we could
see how the children were getting along here.
That's not possible.
We had to transfer the children.
They will be going to a facility that's better equipped.
Okay. Which facility?
I'm sorry, but I can't disclose that information.
You'll just have to take my word
that they'll be well taken care of.
From here on out, MAR will be
responsible for their treatment.
And another thing.
Haru'ue will be staying with us.
What? But, why?
Well, as you know, she's spent a long
time waiting to see her friend again.
She wants to stay by her side.
Really?
Here, pick one.
Um... one, what?
Why, a color...
If the color you choose is the one that comes
out, I'll let you see Haru'ue and the others.
Well... um...
So indecisive!
Well, why don't we choose yellow?
Here.
Aw, it's a brown one.
What a shame, huh?
This is no time to be playing games!
Oh, I'm not playing at anything.
Uh-oh... I'm so sorry about that.
I don't understand.
What's going on?
Oh, well. It's not as if the
data will be of any use anyway.
Director Kihara, it's about time.
One moment.
Kihara?
Oh, you mean you didn't know that?
That's my middle name, you see.
Kihara.
In full, Therestina Kihara Lifeline.
Why, you...!
Dr. Kiyama! Are you okay?
Say something please!
We're terribly busy, you understand.
I hope you won't mind if I ask you to show yourselves out.
Here, have some tea.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Well, why wouldn't I be?
It's a relief to have the
poltergeisting case closed, finally.
We can go back to our everyday lives again.
Uh-huh...
I know you guys have been a
little bit out of sorts lately,
but now everything can get back to normal.
Isn't that right, Shirai?
I haven't behaved any differently than usual.
Here.
I know! I'll give Uiharu a call and see
when Haru'ue is getting out of the hospital.
It is practically the height of summer.
We should enjoy it.
You're right about that.
Hey, Uiharu. It's Saten.
Where are you?
S... S... Saten...
What's wrong?
It's...
Oh...
Saten!
What's the matter?
Uiharu!
Come on, I can't understand through all the sniffling.
What is it?
Finally, this is it.
I've finished gathering all the
material about the poltergeisting.
Well, go ahead and get rid of it.
I got a call from the MAR laboratory just now.
They said they have all the information they require.
Aw, man. This took me so long!
Did they say anything more?
Nope. They said "it's over now" and left it at that.
Doesn't that seem a little... unusual?
Her name's Therestina Kihara?
Are you sure that's what she said?
And Kiyama, what about her?
I don't know.
She went... somewhere...
Take it easy.
It's gonna be okay.
Huh?
Found her.
Yes, Therestina Kihara Lifeline.
Gensei Kihara's granddaughter.
Oh, my.
What, is there more?
She's included in the personnel data from
Kihara's lab, from the time he wrote his thesis.
What does that mean?
Therestina was Kihara's research assistant?
That would make sense, wouldn't it?
Wait a second!
What is it?
Therestina was the first test
subject for the ability crystal.
How can that be?
Whoa, let me get this straight.
You're telling me Kihara's first human
experiment was on his own granddaughter
and that Therestina helped with his research?
The same woman who has the
Child Errors under her protection?
What's going on?!
Don't ask me! I'm just as confused as anybody.
What... What do we do?
I can't believe it!
How is this happening?
Please try to stop crying.
I can't!
Haru'ue... Edasaki... all the other children...
It's okay.
What now?
I've failed them all!
What do I do?
Tell me, how much longer are
you going to sit there, crying?
You.. hit me...
Isn't there something more useful you could be doing?
When are you going to get a hold of
yourself and act like a Judgment officer again?
Let me take over.
If you want.
Checking for probable locations
where the children would have been sent.
Where's Misaka?
Sissy...
Here.
You can use this to dry off.
Great, thanks a lot!
I can't believe Kongo's been
in the hospital this entire time.
It seems excessive.
Is her condition really that serious?
I'm kind of worried about her.
Maybe we should go pay her a visit, then.
Yeah, good idea.
Ignore her. Keep moving.
I should tell you.
The children were aboard the
trucks that passed by just now.
Don't you want to go after them?
You tricked us.
Are you angry?
I want to know what you've got up your sleeve.
You make it sound so sinister.
You are Gensei Kihara's granddaughter.
You were also the first test
subject for the ability crystal.
Used as a lab rat by your own flesh and blood.
And yet, you're still assisting
with your grandfather's research.
Using the children as you were used.
So, tell me, what are you planning?!
You've done your homework, haven't you.
But what you still don't seem to realize is
that I don't answer to anybody other than myself.
Moron!
And now you're going to try forcing me to reveal my plans.
That sound.
It's Capacity Down!
You're familiar with it, then?
Why do you have it, though?
Why wouldn't I have it?
I am its creator, after all!
You are?
As it happens, I gathered a lot of helpful information
from loaning it out to those idiots in Skill Out.
So this new version is significantly more powerful.
Though that did require making
the device a good deal larger.
Apparently, even a band of fools
like Skill Out can be somewhat useful.
Stop screwing around with me.
Huh?
Using Skill Out, too?!
They aren't your lab rats!
No need for hysterics.
I missed.
Calibration's a bit off
but I guess that'll just draw the fun out a little longer.
Why, you!
My power...
Poor girl. Haven't you noticed that
none of your attacks are reaching me?
Keep running, my darling Level
Five, but it won't do you any good.
Goodness. What on earth is going on out there?
All that smoke.
It looks like a disaster area.
Huh? Isn't that.
It's Misaka!
People like you and your friends
are such fascinating specimens.
In thrall to your own naive sense of justice.
I owe you my gratitude.
It's all thanks to you that I was
able to track down the test subjects.
As a reward, I'll let you in on a little secret.
I needed access to those children because
I intend to perfect the ability crystal.
No... You... can't...
Oh, can't I?
Who's going to stand in my way?
We've got a new candidate for experimentation.
Someone take her away.
Just a moment!
I'll have you know, that girl
you're carrying is a friend of mine.
And you do not want to cross Mitsuko
Kongo of Tokiwadai Middle School!
All units, report status.
Yellow Marble. Good to go.
Brown Marble. Good to go.
All units, you are clear to proceed as planned...
This is Blue Marble reporting.
We've lost Railgun!
You what?!
I apologize.
We're currently searching the surrounding area.
We'll find her.
Never mind!
But I will not soon forget today's incompetence!
Sissy!
Misaka! Are you all right?
How do you feel? Are you hurt at all?
I'm confused...
What happened?
Well, I'm not one to brag, but
it all worked out, thanks to me.
I'm certain you'd love to hear all about my heroic
rescue but really, there isn't that much to tell.
Oh, all right, if you insist.
I'd hate to deprive you of a
thrilling tale of selflessness.
Really? So Kongo saved me?
Therestina.
Sit back down, Sissy.
You need to rest some more.
Get out of my way.
I don't have time to be lounging around in bed now.
I need to go.
I have to help the children!
You're staying here, Sissy.
What a fool! I snuck into the
laboratory on my own and lost my temper.
I found the children, but I led
Therestina straight to them as well.
And now they're all gone.
They're gone, and it's entirely my fault.
Don't you see?
I have to stop her and make this right.
So stand aside, Kuroko.
What are you doing?
Misaka...
I want you to stop for a minute.
Look around and tell me what you see.
What are you talking about?
I see you, standing there.
I'm sorry.
Really.
You're right.
I was... I was being selfish.
And... I've gone and caused trouble for you all again.
It isn't any trouble.
Really. But I'd rather fight together with you
than worry about you out there all on your own again.
You know. That's what friends are for, isn't it?
Saten's right!
You're not alone. You've got all of us!
Yeah, I know I do.
Thanks, you guys.
You're next, Uiharu.
You'll apologize to Shirai.
Tell her you're sorry for the way
you've been treating her through all this!
Hey, hold on! That's not fair!
You, too, Shirai...
Apologize to Uiharu for slapping her!
I'm sorry for how I've behaved.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
So? Don't you have something to say to me, as well?
Yes, I do. Thanks, Kongo.
Oh, it was nothing, really.
We now have irrefutable evidence that
Therestina Kihara is involved in illegal activities.
We've always suspected there was
something suspicious about her organization.
We're looking into her, too...
We don't have any time to waste.
We need to be doing something!
Can't Antiskill help out?
It isn't that easy for us to get involved.
There are limits to what we can do.
Oh, yeah? What about finding the
strength to overcome your limits?
It's you... from the workshop.
You're the one who said that when you convince
yourself you can't do any more, you're finished.
Well, we can't give up. Not now.
The children need us!
Okay. Give me a little time.
I'm receiving satellite surveillance data from Antiskill.
The MAR trailers are on Urban Expressway Five, just
passing the interchange for School District Eighteen.
Urban Expressway Five.
That leads to District Seventeen, doesn't it?
Why District Seventeen?
Do they have some reason for heading there?
I think so.
Gensei Kihara had a private lab in that area.
Well, let's see.
Here. Can you zoom in enough to
see what's behind the trailers?
Sure.
Dr. Kiyama!
Geez, she's going after them on her own?
How can she take this all on herself?
Really, Sissy?
You know it's almost impossible
not to say something sarcastic now.
Yeah, it sounds like you've
got a lot in common with Kiyama.
Hey, now. That isn't true.
So, is there something I'm supposed to be doing here?
Huh? Oh, are you still around?
Here, wash it down with this.
We can't fight on empty stomachs, can we?
Now eat up, everyone!
Right!
Huh? What is this recording?
All right, then.
Let's get going!
We've got work to do!
We'll defeat Therestina...
find Haru'ue... and Kiyama...
And then...
We'll save the children!