This is true.
The events I'm about to describe actually happened
to our friend's sister's roommate's boyfriend.
It was a sultry summer evening, and this
boyfriend of hers was strolling through a park.
There was no sign of anyone else in the area.
A lone woman appeared and came up to
him asking how to get the train station.
The boyfriend was a polite young man, and
he graciously began giving her directions.
As he did, the woman stared at him with a vacant
look in her eyes and started slowly lifting her hands.
Then, suddenly, there was a great whoosh!
Why was there a whoosh?
The strange woman removed her blouse.
Please! That was the least scary story ever!
We did a lot to create a creepy atmosphere,
but I don't think anything can save that story.
Huh?
It really happened to someone
we know. How is that not freaky?
The legend of the Undress-tress
who disrobes without warning!
No, not scary.
It's more like a story about a sicko
who could use some serious therapy.
Then how about another one?
This site is full of different stories.
"When you see the wind turbines spin
backwards, it's a sign of the apocalypse.
Doom is just around the corner!"
"Don't cross between districts at
four-forty-four in the afternoon.
You'll find yourself in the
Imaginary Number School District!"
It says there's the tool that'll instantly
increase your ability- The Level Upper!
This is getting ridiculous. Would you
stop looking at that stupid site already?
Urban legends are useless. They
have no basis in scientific fact.
This is Academy City after all.
Geez, you have no sense of adventure.
Besides, sometimes these stories are based
on real events that have just gotten twisted
until they become crazy legends.
Look at this one.
"The boy with the power to
prevent other powers from working."
That's a story you'd only hear in Academy City.
The power to prevent other powers from working?
That's the most absurd one we've heard!
Nobody could have that ability.
Please! Don't you agree, Sissy?
Yeah, totally crazy.
But if someone like that did
exist, I'd sure like to fight him.
But, of course, he doesn't. So...
Even more urban legends, huh?
A boy who somehow has the power to
prevent other powers from working.
Of all things.
We got ourselves a cutie here.
Oooh, and she's from Tokiwadai, too.
Wanna come with us? Have some fun tonight?
We'll even take you back to your dorm. Of course,
there's no telling how late it might be by then.
What do these idiots think they're
going to accomplish by talking to me?
Pathetic.
Everyone else is pretending not to see.
It's not that they don't care.
They just can't do anything about it.
If they interfered, they'd only get themselves hurt.
And that wouldn't help anyone.
Everyone has to look out for
themselves. That's the way it works.
And if there is somebody out there who would
jump in the middle of this to help out a stranger.
Well, that person is just a fool.
Oh, hey! There you are!
Thanks for keeping her company, guys!
You shouldn't wander off like
that. You know how much I worry!
Okay! Thanks, again!
You mind telling me who you are?
Why couldn't you just play along? The plan was I pretend
to be your friend and casually walk you away from here.
And now that's ruined!
Why should I follow a convoluted
plan from some random guy?
Who do you think you are, punk?
Think you can make us look like fools?
Yeah, dude, you got some kinda problem with us?
No, I just...
What's the use, really?
Yeah, I've got a problem.
You guys don't have any shame, do you?
All of you ganging up like this
on a single, helpless young girl?
It's pathetic! I mean, have you taken a
good look at her? She's basically a kid.
You heard her talking to me. She sounded like a
child who hasn't learned how to respect her elders.
She looks sweet, but she still
hasn't outgrown her rebellious phase.
That's how young she is!
And besides that, you can't even face this
defenseless child unless you gang up on her?
You guys make me sick!
You wanna know what's making
me sick right now, Wonder Boy?
You are!
I just can't understand it.
Why don't my shocks work on him?
Could it really be like that urban legend says?
No, impossible!
If I hit him with my full force, he'd be toast.
Next time I run into him, I'll...
Can you remember any landmarks or anything?
Landmarks?
Hm. Well, there was a crosswalk in front of it, I think.
That's not really a landmark.
There are kind of a lot of them here.
It's you!
Oh. Hey, Bug Zapper. What's up?
Don't call me that! I'm Mikoto Misaka!
And today is the day I'm gonna settle the score with you!
Okay, that's nice.
So does that mean you aren't busy right now?
If it's time you want, I've got plenty to spare.
Good deal.
Then do you think you could help this
woman find where she parked her car?
Huh?
Yeah. I know I parked it in a lot around here some
place, but I can't figure out exactly where it was.
Uh, hold on.
Why me?
Well, there's somewhere important that I need to be now.
You've got time, so it's fine, right?
No, actually, it isn't fine!
You want to weasel out of this,
but I'm not going to let you!
And don't try to come up with some lame
excuse again, because it isn't going to work.
Wow. It sure is hot out, don't you think?
What... what are you doing that for?
I've been walking around in the
blazing sun for quite a while now.
I'm dripping with sweat.
What is with this woman?
I have no idea. I just met her a few minutes ago.
Anyway, lady, would you please put your shirt back on?
That woman is being assaulted!
Huh? Is that boy ripping off her clothes?
I think he is!
No, really.
Huh?
You've got it all wrong!
Hey, get back here!
Excuse me...
If you're going to run off, could you
at least give me my shirt back, please?
Whatever, hurry up and put it back on, okay?
People are starting to stare!
That was refreshing. I feel so much better now.
What's the deal with that woman?
Just randomly stripping her clothes off in public?
Huh? It really happened to someone
we know. How is that not freaky?
The legend of the Undresstress
who disrobes without warning!
No way, that was just a story.
Hello?
Hey, Sissy! Where are you right now? Are you busy?
I was about to go have tea with Uiharu and Saten.
You're welcome to come along if you'd like.
Well, the thing is, I'm stuck helping out this weird lady.
Weird? How so?
She started stripping off her clothes without any warning?
She's stripping! It's the Undresstress. It has to be!
Oh, no, Misaka! Will you be okay?
Let go! Please!
Could you two try to get it together?
Text me her picture, okay? I want documentation!
Get a grip, you guys.
Don't go thinking she's something from an urban legend.
She might seem a little odd, but
I'm sure she's just an ordinary...
You said somebody is odd?
Is it me you're talking about?
No. Of course not. I mean, you did take off your shirt.
Well...
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a message at the tone.
That seems a little bit suspicious, don't you think?
Shouldn't we track Misaka down
and make sure that she's okay?
You're really taking this urban legend seriously.
How incredibly childish.
To thank you for keeping me company.
Oh, all right. Thank you.
Why something hot?
Especially curry soup?
Most people don't realize this, but when
it's hot out, a warm drink is better for you.
Also, curry contains special spices that
help to relieve fatigue and rejuvenate the body.
I think I understand the theory of what you're saying.
But, emotionally, I find a cold drink
on a hot day more satisfying, so...
Emotionally? Huh.
I suppose when you're younger, emotions tend
to drive your decisions more than practicality.
I'll get you something else. What would you like?
Oh, no. Please, that's okay. The sentiment is enough.
Sorry about that.
I tend to look at things from a logical perspective
maybe because of all the time I spend doing research.
You do a lot of research?
Are you some kind of scientist, then?
I'm a cerebrophysiologist.
My primary area of study is AIM diffusion fields.
Diffusion fields.
Those are the weak spheres of power that Espers
continuously emit without being consciously aware of it?
That's right. You've already learned about them in school?
Uh... huh. Back during my first year.
They told us the fields are so weak
they can't be detected with human senses and
have to be measured using specialized devices.
I'm especially interested in discovering
ways to harness and apply that power.
Oh, does that mean...
Do you know a lot about Esper abilities?
Are you interested in something specific?
Well, yeah,
Um... Is it possible that there's an ability
that can negate other powers?
Well, there are so many different abilities out there.
Can you give me a clearer
example of what you're describing?
Let's say someone was hit with an
electric shock and it had no effect.
An electric shock, huh?
Maybe this person generated something to act as a
lightning rod and deflected the electrical current?
It's something different than that.
I'm not really sure how to explain it.
Is this person an acquaintance of yours?
Oh! No!
It's an urban legend my friends were talking about.
It's ridiculous. I shouldn't have said anything.
An urban legend, huh?
Is that the kind of thing children
are interested in these days?
I know it sounds silly, but there
are quite a few of them going around.
Y'know, like the Undresstress?
Undresstress?
No, never mind. Forget I even mentioned it!
Oh! I'm so sorry!
No, don't worry about it.
It'll wash off easily enough.
Can't you keep your clothes on?
Still no answer.
Why can't I get a hold of her?
Probably 'cause the Undresstress is attacking her!
I'm not listening to that nonsense.
Look what I found.
This website has a ton of detailed information on it.
And it's all about her.
Let me see.
What is it? What does it say?
It's terrible.
It says here the victims of the
Undresstress may try to hold out,
but all eventually utter a final cry and are lost forever.
This gets more absurd every second.
It's just a dumb story.
But, if you're that worried,
remember that Sissy is the ultimate,
unstoppable shock princess, the Ace of Tokiwadai.
She's hardly going to be undone by some strange
woman just because she likes to undress in public.
That's not all.
I think something even more
terrifying could be happening here.
Now what are you going on about?
What if the Undresstress is contagious somehow?
What? You mean like a disease?
Maybe those who meet her become cursed the way she is.
Maybe they become Undresstresses, too!
Then Misaka will go around stripping for everybody!
Oh, no. That can't happen. Not to my Sissy!
No! Don't do it, Sissy! You can't!
Um, Shirai?
Uiharu, you have to find a way to lift the curse!
Right now!
Please, don't get so worked up. You're hurting me!
Yeah, remember?
It's nothing but an urban legend, right?
Sorry for inconveniencing you so much.
Well, I've already come this far.
There you go.
Great. Thank you.
Oh, yes. Thank that young man for me, too, won't you?
Young man?
He's a friend of yours, right?
He could tell I was in trouble
and asked what he could do to help.
Oh, did he?
He's a good kid.
He's always butting in.
I think he just likes to play the hero.
He barges into the middle of a situation,
babbling random stuff, and then disappears again.
It's annoying.
I don't know how to describe it, but
something about him rubs me the wrong way.
He's headstrong and naive.
It's like he stepped out of a fairy tale.
He's always convinced that he's...
He sounds like a fun guy.
So are you, you know, in love with this kid?
What? You're crazy!
You know what I'm talking about.
That thing where you pretend to hate
someone but, really, you're nuts about them?
What do they call it again?
Let's see, here.
Ah, yes. Playing hard to get.
That's it.
That's impossible!
What's happening? Why'd the alarm go off?
No time to ask questions.
Come on, let's go!
Move.
Thanks so much for helping me.
Take care, okay?
'Kay. Drive safely!
Come to think of it, who forgets
where they parked their car?
There's definitely something off about her, all right.
I'm exhausted.
It's not like I did all that
much today. Why am I so worn out?
This is his fault. He ruined my day.
Next time I see him I swear I'll...
They all broke!
A week's worth of breakfast, just gone!
This is awful.
I waited in line for two hours!
I can't believe it! This is why you ran away earlier?
You saddled me with some crazy
exhibitionist lady so you could go shopping?
You know, for a student as poor as I am, getting groceries
while they're on sale can be a matter of life and death!
Not that somebody from Tokiwadai would understand!
I didn't have an awesome day either, thank you!
Her skirt got dirty, so she stripped again,
and I had to wash it, and after all that.
She told me I was playing...
What?
Never mind. Just forget about it. You owe me a fight!
I don't get why you're so eager for another fight.
You've lost every one so far, haven't you?
Shut up!
I haven't been giving it everything
I've got yet, so I haven't lost anything.
Okay. How are we going to resolve this?
Huh? Well, it's a simple matter, really.
I just have to beat you up.
Quit with the sighing, already. It's irritating me!
All right, I give.
If it's the only thing that will satisfy you.
I'm willing to take you on.
Good. I'm glad you finally came around.
We shouldn't bother anybody if we fight down here.
I'm ready when you are.
So bring it on.
You don't have to tell me twice.
I've been waiting a long time for this opportunity.
All right, here we go!
Like I thought. Shocks don't work on you.
Well, then...
Huh? What's that thing?
Whoa! Hey, now.
Isn't it against the rules to use weapons?
Not if I made it using my ability.
The iron sand vibrates, making it sort of like a chainsaw.
Fair warning, it might hurt a bit if it touches you.
I'm really not okay with this.
Do you think you could put that thing away?
You can dodge and duck and run all you want.
No matter how far you scamper, I can still reach you!
It's longer!
Gotcha! Let's see if you can dodge this!
He deflected the sand particles back at me!
Oh, well. I anticipated that, too.
Well, looks like that's the match, huh?
Oh, no.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Uh... oh. Even in the wind she can control it?
No matter how many times you try it's
going to end the same way it always has.
I've got you! You can stop my currents in mid-air,
but...
My electricity!
It isn't even flowing!
How does this guy do it?
Uh...
Yeah. I give up. You're the winner.
Jerk! Don't screw with me!
Take this fight seriously!
I'm trying to help. You looked really scared!
No I didn't. You don't scare me!
Now you're lying!
Your eyes got all red and watery like a baby.
Then you flinched.
Die!
Get back here!
Be careful! If that had hit me
directly, it could have killed me!
You know full well it wouldn't have hurt you!
Whether it would have worked on me or not,
you've gotta be pretty sick to send an
attack like that without even hesitating.
I'll have you know I've never used that much
of my power to attack somebody before today!
Then why start now? Why me?
Quit running like a little girl and face me!
Just leave me alone. I didn't ask for this!
Hey, I'm back.
Huh? Kuroko isn't home yet?
I'm exhausted.
So, it's true then.
Kuroko? Where are you hiding?
You were stripping off all your clothing.
Saten was right. You really
were cursed by the Undresstress!
Here!
It's imperative that you put
these on your head immediately!
Geez. What's gotten into you now?
This is the only way to lift the evil curse.
The curse of the vile Undresstress!
Undresstress, I banish you!
Put those down! Have you gone insane?
I banish you!
Curse, be gone!
So, she's the Level 5.
I've heard so much about her.
What a fascinating young girl.
I had fun today, and as an added
bonus, I get to do the preview.
Let's see. I think I'll accompany the preview
with some tasteful disrobing. Next time...
Don't you dare!