From what we've learned today, it should be apparent
that this aspect of Academy City's
ability-developing curriculum is the most important.
Personal Reality.
To put it another way,
it is the acquiring of a reality unto oneself.
This is the basis for the development of Esper powers.
Once you understand Personal Reality, you
must begin to explore quantum theory as well.
This concept is based on the uncertainty principle
postulated by the German physicist Heisenberg.
Now, Personal Reality and quantum theory are
connected because they have something in common.
Both concepts are rooted in probability.
For example, let's look at Schrodinger's cat.
Huh? A cold?
Yeah. I only have a slight
fever, but it won't seem to budge.
Okay.
Try to get some rest and feel better.
Saten!
Ruiko Saten!
Uh, yes?
You look like you already know the material.
Maybe you'd like to explain that last point to the class.
Oh, sure!
Let's see.
One sec.
Never mind.
I suggest you study up on Personal Reality for next time.
That's all for today.
Who cares about theories and thought experiments?
I wish they'd teach us how to level up faster.
That would be useful.
It's really hot out today, isn't it?
What's with the face? You look super grouchy.
I can't believe that Hatsuya Kaitabi was a
Level 2. It just doesn't make any sense to me.
Kaitabi?
Oh.
The guy behind the graviton attacks.
But, all of the destruction,
he would have to be at least a Level 4 to cause that.
Right. And that can only mean one thing.
Well, it has to mean...
I have no idea. What does it mean?
Hey, don't look at me.
That's kinda what I was asking you.
You're stressing. Let's take a break.
It might help you to cool off.
What do you want?
Just whatever you're having, Sissy.
You know what I've always found strange?
How whenever you hear a wind chime,
it makes you feel a little bit cooler.
Yeah. It does that because of synesthesia.
What's synesthesia?
Thank you for waiting.
Here you go. Two strawberries.
It's the reception of multiple
sensations from a single stimulus.
And we're paying separately, by the way.
You were the one who suggested it.
I thought it was your treat.
Huh? What's that?
Oh, nothing at all.
So, anyway, seeing reddish
colors makes you feel warmer, right?
And in the same way, seeing
bluish tones makes you feel cooler.
Reds are warm colors, whereas blues are cool colors.
Right. And this shaved ice is strawberry-red.
I get it.
The fact that it's such a bright red
intensifies the fruitiness of the sensation.
Did your brain freeze?
Aw.
Misaka Shirai! Hey you guys!
Hey, Saten.
Those ices look delicious.
Yeah, we feel your pain.
That happened to both of us a second ago.
You know what's going to happen,
but you can't stop eating it.
Ooh. Did you guys get strawberry?
Mm... hmm.
Here, would you like to taste?
Aw, that's so nice of you.
Don't mind if I do!
Mmm, yummy!
Let me give you a bite of lemon in return.
Cool, thank you.
What? What do you think you're doing?
Uh, tasting each other's flavors.
You're tasting her flavor.
Tasting.
Flavor.
I could have done that!
Kuroko, you're a complete idiot!
Oh, okay.
Then why don't you kiss my...
I mean taste my flavor, too?
What would be the point? You got the same flavor I did.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I am such a moron!
Hey, I just realized Uiharu isn't with you today.
She stayed home from school
because, apparently, she's got a cold.
I was just on my way to drop off some medicine for her.
Is it really bad?
No. She doesn't think it's anything serious,
but I know how annoying colds can be.
You know, you guys could come along, too.
Here we are!
We all wanted to check up on you.
Hope it isn't a bad time.
Thanks guys. That's sweet.
Don't worry about it.
Now, hold still.
It says 37 point three.
Well, that's slightly high, so
you should probably stay in bed.
And be sure to cover up so you don't catch a chill.
You know, Saten, it might help prevent a chill
if you'd stop flipping my skirt up all the time.
Don't give them the wrong idea!
As Uiharu's best friend,
I just want to make sure she's wearing panties every day
like she's supposed to. It's my duty.
Of course I wear panties! Every day!
Yes, of course. We know you do.
Now lie down before you get any worse.
I'll go fix up a cool towel for you.
Oh, I wanted to ask you, Shirai,
have there been any developments
in the graviton attacker case?
There is one thing, I guess.
It isn't really much help, though.
We know that the person who's responsible
for the attacks has a Level 2 ranking.
But what he did was unmistakably Level 4 stuff.
So the only development so far is the discovery
that there's even more we don't understand about it?
Yeah, that's pretty much it.
Now that I think about it, didn't you mention
something before about a machine called the Level Upper?
Huh?
It raises a person's ability level?
Yeah, but like I said, it's just a rumor
all totally unsubstantiated.
So there's no proof it exists?
None at all.
The stories about it are all mixed up.
It's nothing more than an urban legend, really.
Oh, well.
I suppose there's no way it
could be that convenient, is there?
The truth is, this isn't the first time a person's Level
as shown in the databank doesn't
match what they've actually done.
We've seen situations like this more than once.
Uhh?
That girl with the funny eyebrows and the stun gun
and the bank robber who was a pyrokineticist.
I use those as examples because they're
ones you already know about, Sissy.
But Judgment has recorded even more instances
of an Esper's ability not matching their attack.
Are you saying?
There really is such a thing as a Level Upper somewhere?
Is there anything else you can tell us about it?
Huh? Let me see.
There is something, but it could be another rumor.
I heard somewhere about people who use the Level Upper
posting to some kind of message board on the net.
Do you know which message board it is?
Um, let me think.
I don't know. Let's see.
Take a look, Saten.
Could it be this one?
Ah, there it is!
Nicely done, Uiharu!
Now if we can only determine their
identities and where they hang out.
I can't speak to their identities,
but as for their hangouts, look.
They seem to get together at
this restaurant pretty frequently.
Thanks a lot, Uiharu.
I'm gonna look into it.
Oh, and get well soon!
Get back here!
This is a job for me! Not you!
Sissy! Listen to me when I'm talking to you!
Sissy!
Do you think they're gonna be okay?
With those two, we don't have anything to worry about.
I mean, Kuroko's a Level 4, and Misaka is a Level 5.
What could they need us for, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Say, Uiharu,
what if we could get a hold of the Level Upper?
Do you think we could really use
it to increase our ability levels?
Who knows?
But in any case, cheating is wrong.
Yeah, I know.
Just hypothetically.
I would never actually do it, of course.
Hey! I've got an idea!
The teacher called on me at school
today, and I had no clue how to answer.
Think you could explain this to me?
I'm sick and you're asking me
to help you do your schoolwork?
I bet you're hungry.
I could make something for you.
And now you're trying to bribe
me with the promise of food?
All right, then. Fine.
I won't ask again.
Well, I guess I could eat.
So, anyway.
He told me to study up on Personal Reality,
but I just don't get the concept, you know?
Yeah, it's complicated.
I feel like I've heard something about it before, though.
You have to create a reality unto yourself.
A reality unto oneself?
A reality unto you.
A reality unto me.
What are these realities, anyway?
Delusions, maybe?
Oh. That might be it.
Huh?
Well, not delusions exactly.
Those are totally unreal.
But what about the assumptions we make about the world.
The power of our own belief?
The power of our own belief, huh?
I'm only a Level 1, though.
I'm sure somebody else could explain it better.
That was great.
I mean, when you first used
the phrase "reality unto oneself,"
I was confused.
But I feel like I'm starting to understand.
Maybe I just have to believe enough
and then my Level will go up someday.
You'll be fine, Saten. I know you.
You're too stubborn to give up easily.
Sometimes you say the rudest things.
You know that?
This is it.
Well, shall we go in?
Sissy, this doesn't concern you.
Maybe but the people we're looking for
might recognize you as a member of Judgment.
But, I...
Look, it'll be fine.
Just let me handle it, okay?
You lay low at another table and wait for me.
What's she planning to do?
I've got a bad feeling about this idea.
Okay, here I go!
No, hold on!
Please don't go in there, Sissy!
You came here looking for
information on the Level Upper, huh?
I came across your message board
and I thought it was super interesting,
so I came here to ask about it
because I know this is where you guys hang out.
Please! I'm begging you!
So, will you tell me?
Don't know what you're talkin' about.
Now scram already.
Come on, I'm not asking very much.
You're buggin' us.
Shouldn't a squirt like you be in bed by now?
This isn't working.
I knew from the beginning it was going to fail.
Hey, now. I'm not as young as I look!
You don't look like such a
little girl from where I'm sitting.
As a matter of fact, you're just my type.
Aw! You really mean it?
So about the Level Upper.
Don't get ahead of yourself, sweetie.
That kinda information doesn't come cheap, you know.
Oh. Well, I guess I have a little money I can give you.
Yeah, money is great and all,
but I actually had another form of
payment in mind, if you get what I'm saying.
Hey now, don't get the wrong impression.
I'm not that kind of girl.
I mean, I only just met you tonight after all.
Are you sure money won't do?
What was that earlier about not being a little girl?
I'm... I'm in a really rough spot right now.
What's going on with all the sniffling?
I don't know what to do.
I don't have anywhere else to
turn other than the Level Upper.
So, please.
Won't you help me?
Whatever, just quit crying.
I'm just, I'm just so...
That uniform.
Isn't it from Tokiwadai?
Yeah, now that you mention it.
If we play it right
she could make for a seriously good money tree.
Hey, uh...
All right, kid.
Quit crying. It's irritating me.
We'll give you the information.
Really? Thanks so much!
We should step outside.
We're not gonna say anything about it in here.
Let's go.
Okay, then.
This is far enough.
Nobody's going to interfere with us out here.
Great!
Why don't you start by giving
us all the cash you've got on you?
Oh, and you can hand over your
debit card and PIN number, too.
And any credit cards, of course.
Being a Tokiwadai lady, I'm sure you've got a few.
Um, well, I did withdraw some cash before I came here,
but I can't just give it all to you.
Oh?
You wanna hear what we have to say?
Then you'd better hurry and pay up.
Do it now.
Give us every last dime you've got
unless you want us to strip search
you and get your money that way.
How annoying.
Look, just hand over the money or we'll...
Whoa! Are you okay?
You! You little brat!
I've had enough of this.
I was trying to go about this in a more civilized manner,
but you guys had to go and get nasty.
Now tell me everything you know about the Level Upper.
I'd change my tone if I were you,
though we're happy to show you
just what our powered-up strength can do.
More of them.
Have all these guys really used this Level Upper thing?
With this many of them at the same Level as Kaitabi...
Yeah, I'm gonna give it to you now.
Take my Level 2...
There were a lot of you guys to deal with.
I'm afraid things were bound to get a little messy.
You really did a number on them, didn't you?
It... it's the boss!
Hey, what's going on?
What were you trying to do to that little lady over there?
We're sorry, Boss.
Shamelessly trying to steal a young girl's money?
But, Boss...
Are you talking back to me? To me?
I... I'm sorry!
I'm not the one you need to apologize to.
Go on, all of you!
Uh, my bad. Sorry.
That's not gonna cut it.
I sincerely apologize.
Us, too!
Well, that should square things, right?
I hope you can forgive them.
You guys! Get out of here!
Ma'am! We're going!
All right. So you're their boss?
In that case, you must know
all about the Level Upper, too.
Let's set that aside.
You gave my underlings a serious working over.
I hope you're prepared to answer for that.
Prepared to...
but, uh...
you just made them apologize to me.
Well, that was that, and now this is this.
Honor demands that I pay you back for what you did.
Let's go!
Whoa! What's happening?
The ground's shifting.
That would be my ability.
It's called Flux Coat.
With it, I have the power to
control the viscosity of the asphalt.
Whatcha gonna do?
There's nowhere to run.
Nice try, girl, but that attack won't... What the?
She vanished!
That wasn't bad.
Impossible! How are you staying up there?
An electrical current.
It creates a magnetic field.
All I have to do is direct it
toward the rebar in the wall.
I'll show you!
Well?
Do you feel like telling me what
you know yet, or shall we continue?
I see now.
You didn't put all the power of your
ability into your first attack, did you?
And just now you intentionally missed me
with that blast as well.
Exactly.
Now, be a good girl and tell me...
Screw you! I'm not declaring defeat yet!
If you call yourself an Esper, give me your best!
You want to try your will against mine?
You think a little electric shock can beat me?
Then go ahead and try. We'll see who wins!
That sounds like a challenge.
Well, I'm happy to take you up on it.
Sissy, hold on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
No, I really don't think you do!
Stop, Sissy!
Come on, Uiharu, admit it.
You want to become a higher-level Esper, too.
You know, like Misaka and Shirai.
Well, having a high ability level would be pretty awesome,
and it would offer a lot of
opportunities for academic advancement.
It's why we're here.
If we wanted a normal school experience,
we could get that anywhere else.
People flock to this city because
they're fascinated by Esper powers.
That's the reason it exists.
Before I came here
I wondered what my ability would turn out to be;
what kind of secret power I could have hidden in me.
I couldn't sleep the night before I
left I was so excited about it all.
And then I had my first System Scan, and they told me,
"You have absolutely no discernible talent.
You are a Level Zero, Saten."
That was hard to hear.
Really hard.
It made me sad.
I know how you feel.
I really do.
I don't have much of an ability level myself, you know.
I'm a One.
But look at the friends I've made.
I get to work side by side with Shirai.
And you and I have fun all the time.
I mean, if I hadn't come here,
I never would have gotten the
chance to meet all of you guys.
So, as far as I'm concerned, coming here
was a worthwhile experience if only for that.
Uiharu.
You're adorable!
Sometimes you say the sweetest things, you know that?
And to say thank you, I'll sponge bathe your entire body!
That's okay! I can reach.
I don't need help!
A blackout?
This is why I was trying to tell you not to do it.
It's not my fault, is it?
How was I supposed to know
that there was something like this around here?
Like I said, I knew there was.
You can't just show up at the last second like that!
And what am I gonna do about my shoes?
I'd say that's your problem.
I guess I lost after all.
So much for that plan.
All that and I didn't end up with any information.
Kuroko!
Come on. We've got a new problem on our hands.
Hatsuya Kaitabi is unconscious?
I don't know all the details.
He suddenly passed out while
Antiskill was questioning him.
Kuroko Shirai, with Judgment.
How is he?
We're doing everything we can, but he
shows no signs of regaining consciousness.
Um, well, I don't know if this
could have something to do with it,
but I punched him pretty hard in the face.
No. He doesn't exhibit any significant head trauma.
For that matter, we can't find
anything wrong with him at all.
We looked him over thoroughly.
He simply lost consciousness.
So you don't know what caused
it or how long it will go on.
There is one unusual thing.
This week we've had multiple patients brought in here
with the same symptoms.
I hate to have to admit it,
but this is beyond the capabilities
of this hospital and its staff.
So, I've called in an outside
specialist in cerebrophysiology.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
I came here at the request of the
Mizuho Systems Hospital Director.
My name is Harumi Kiyama.
Thank you for coming.
Why are you here?
I can't find anything concrete on the Level Upper.
Maybe it really is nothing more than just a rumor.
Guess I'll download some new songs on here.
Is that a hidden link?
Could this be?
The Level Upper actually exists?
Do people who use it ever go back to normal?
Huh? I was talking to you.
Where did you go?
Saten?