The attacks began a week ago and
they have been escalating ever since.
It is a series of Graviton attacks, with each successive
incident the force and scale have both increased.
We cannot find any pattern in the
times and locations of the attacks,
and after examining the psychometry of articles
left behind, we still do not have any leads.
We are working with anti-skill
to prevent anymore casualties.
We have increased security that we must do
everything we can to get this case solved.
Are you sure you're feeling okay?
You were up late again last night
investigating those serial attacks.
It's the only thing I can think to do.
The search is still turning up nothing.
For now, I'm just checking to make
sure we haven't overlooked anything.
Well, it's great you're so committed to your work and all,
but you shouldn't push yourself so hard.
Aw! Thank you, Sissy!
It warms my heart to know you're so concerned about me.
I think what would really help is if we
could sleep in the same bed together tonight.
My fatigue would evaporate immediately!
Aw, man!
Well, the least you can do is wait for me, Sissy.
Really, must you always be so coy?
AIM diffusion fields are localized
phenomena that occur only around Espers.
Of course, AIM is an acronym. It
stands for "An Involuntary Movement."
An AIM diffusion field is a weak force that
Espers involuntarily emit around themselves.
It can't be felt with the five senses.
Without specialized equipment,
it can't be detected at all.
However, researchers into applications in this
field have been making remarkable progress recently.
Hey! What're you poking me for?
You want to do some shopping
at Seventh Mist on the way home?
Yeah! Oh, I can't.
I still have work to do for Judgment.
You can blow that off for a bit, though, can't you?
Just say we were out patrolling or something.
That won't work.
I really would love to go with you, but
solving this case just matters more right now.
Oh. Okay.
Hey.
We need cash. You gonna lend us some more?
What? I can't.
I mean, I would, but you haven't paid
back what you already borrowed from me.
Huh?
We told you we'd pay you back, didn't we?
Once we've got the dough.
Don't you remember? You're giving us
loans, indefinitely and interest, free.
That was the deal we had.
Is this seriously all you've got?
Come on.
Let's get going before Judgment shows up.
Nothin' to worry about there.
They're too busy with those bombings
to have time for anything else.
Damn it.
He's right. They're useless.
Judgment? Don't make me laugh.
This wouldn't be happening to me if they'd do their job.
But just wait.
Aw, geez!
I wish we had just a little more to go on.
Yeah, tell me about it.
So far all we know is the suspect
is a Level 4 Esper or higher.
We really need more information.
Hm.
And the databank isn't coming
up with a match to the ability.
Maybe it's somebody who's had a very
sudden, dramatic increase in power.
No. No way.
Over such a short period of
time? That would be impossible.
Just wishful thinking.
You're right. Something like that could never happen.
Let's keep at it.
We'll go over the fragments left behind again.
Yeah, good idea!
Saten!
Kuroko's so stressed.
It must be just as hard on Uiharu.
She's working so much!
I asked if she wanted to go shopping with me today.
Of course she said, "No."
Yeah. They don't really have a choice
until this mad bomber is captured.
It all makes me feel...
I don't know.
I feel so insignificant right now.
Oh, how should I put it?
Uiharu and Kuroko are doing so
much work for this Judgment case
and obviously, you're in a league of your own.
And then there's me, and I'm just...
Oh, sorry! Really!
I'm not trying to throw a pity party!
I just mean if I had an ability, too,
it would really change my life, you know?
Aw. If only I had a Level Upper or something,
then maybe I could be a Level 5 someday, too.
What's a Level Upper?
It's one of those urban legends I mentioned before.
Apparently, it's a device that will
automatically upgrade your ability level for you.
When we found out the "Undresstress" was real,
I started thinking maybe it could be real, too.
But that's ridiculous, isn't it?
Say... Let's all go together!
You want me to go shopping with you, Sissy? Really?
You and Uiharu are both off.
I told Saten I thought it would be
fun for all of us to make a day of it.
Oh. You said that, did you?
Well, I appreciate the offer, but
I don't think I'll be able to go.
I still need to do a little bit more investigating.
Oh. Okay, then.
Well, good luck.
I'm going to sleep.
A new world order is on its way.
And this time, I'll be on top.
It's a shame Shirai couldn't make it today.
Oh, she's not coming at all?
Apparently, she still has to work.
Judgment has never done anything to help me.
Who needs them?
Over here! Come on!
So, are you looking for anything specific?
No, but I haven't really thought about it that much.
U... i... ha... ru!
Come look over here!
Uh, at what exactly?
See?
These are great, aren't they?
No! Never, never, never!
On me?
I couldn't get away with those, could I?
Think of how stylish and mature they'd look.
You could show them off proudly
whenever I flip up your skirt.
I don't want to show off.
I don't want my skirt flipped up!
Aw, that's too bad.
Oh, hey!
What are you in the market for today?
Huh? Well, let's see.
Maybe some new pajamas?
In that case, let's head this way.
They sure do have a lot of stuff here.
But I haven't seen anything I like so far.
Over here! These are adorable!
Whoa. Hey, Uiharu.
You've gotta check these pj's out.
When was the last time you saw
anybody wearing something like that?
I had something that looked very similar
back when I was in elementary school.
But that was a while ago.
Well, yeah, of course.
Now that we're in middle school,
we can't wear this type of thing.
Obviously.
Well, I think I'm gonna look at swimsuits.
Yeah, all right.
I'm pretty sure they were back this way.
Cool.
Who cares, anyway?
They're just pajamas, right?
It's not like anyone else will see them.
How about this one? Isn't it pretty?
All right, now's my chance.
Nobody will notice if I take a quick look.
Yoink!
Uh, what are you doing, Zapper?
I'm shopping with friends.
What are you doing here?
What, am I not allowed to be here?
Big Brother!
You're with the nice lady from Tokiwadai!
Oh! The girl with the bag.
I didn't realize you had a younger sister.
Yeah, well, I don't.
This little girl just asked me
to help her find a clothing store.
Seems she's nicknamed me, Big Brother.
Now we're here! Big Brother picked out a perfect store!
I'm gonna dress up real pretty and fancy!
And I'll look just like the grown-ups on TV!
You will, will you?
Well, I think you already look pretty snazzy this way.
Unlike a certain somebody I happen to know.
You want a piece of me?
I'm perfectly happy to settle
what we started the other day.
Huh? You're still worked up?
Is that the only thing you ever think about?
Here? Really?
You actually want to start a
fight in front of all these people?
Hey, hey!
I wanna look there!
Oh? Well, let's go.
Bye... bye, nice lady!
See you!
What's up?
Is something wrong, Misaka?
No. It's nothing.
That guy always makes me lose my temper.
Why does he do that to me?
Gekota!
Never mind. It's not.
It doesn't look much like him at all.
I'm starting to wonder.
Could we have two different
suspects? Both with the same M.O.?
Don't be silly.
I'm grasping at straws.
I just can't see any connection
between all of the attacks.
If we don't figure this out soon, we'll have
another victim on our hands-maybe more than one.
If only we had at least one solid lead.
Nine of our colleagues have been hurt already.
Nine?
What are you thinking?
That seems like an awful lot, don't you think?
Maybe we're the targets!
Accelerated gravitons have been detected!
Uiharu. That's your phone, isn't it?
Oh. Yeah, it is.
Yes, this is Ui...
Uiharu!
Update on the graviton attacks.
The surveillance satellite has picked
up an explosive acceleration of gravitons.
Where is it happening?
Antiskill officers in the area are responding
immediately, but we need you to get back here at once!
Wait, Kuroko. Where is the attack?
A clothing store called Seventh
Mist in the Seventh School District.
Seventh Mist clothing store?
That's perfect, then. That's where I am right now.
I'll start the emergency evacuation!
Uiharu!
Hello? Are you there?
What does she think she's doing?
What's going on? What did she say?
Please listen and don't panic.
We know where the attacker's next target is.
We're standing in it.
Wha... What did you say?
Here's the plan.
I want you to start helping with the evacuation, Misaka.
Yeah. Sure thing.
And Saten-you get to safety, okay?
You'll be careful, too, won't you?
He's got his next target, all right.
Attention all customers.
We are experiencing an electrical
malfunction inside the store.
We sincerely apologize for any
inconvenience this might cause,
but we must immediately suspend business for the day.
Please follow the clerks'
instructions to the nearest exit.
Again, we sincerely apologize for any
inconvenience, but we must immediately suspend business.
Zapper!
Have you seen that little girl?
Huh? I thought she was with you!
I can't find her anywhere.
She could still be inside the store.
What is she doing?
Hey!
Uiharu!
Everyone has been evacuated.
Listen to me. You need to get out of there right now!
The only human casualties in the
past attacks were Judgment members.
The suspect's actual target is any
Judgment officer who's in the area!
And that means that this time
the target is going to be you!
Hey there, lady!
Is that...?
A strange man wearing glasses asked me to
come over and give this to you as a present.
Here!
Get down right now! That thing is a bomb!
I'll railgun it out of here!
Uh... oh!
What was that?
An explosion!
It must be one of those serial bombings!
It looked like there were still people inside!
I think I saw a girl from Judgment.
Everybody! Stand back!
Get back now, people! Clear the area!
Awesome!
That was perfect! Perfect!
I'm controlling stronger and stronger power every time!
I'm getting close. A few more
attacks and I should be ready.
I'll take on Judgment and those
punks at school along with 'em.
I'll blow every last one...
What the... What happened?
Hi!
I assume you know what this is about.
I'm right, aren't I? Mister Mad Bomber?
-No.
I have no idea what you're talking about, really.
Well, there is a lot of property
damage. I'll give you that.
But too bad for you.
There wasn't a single causality.
Nobody suffered even so much as a scratch.
No! That's impossible! I was using the maximum power.
Well, I mean, it looked like
a huge explosion from outside.
So, I seriously doubt anybody still
in the store could have survived it.
It's Railgun.
The great Ace of Tokiwadai.
Just my luck.
It's always like this.
No matter what I do.
People are always beating me down, but I'm gonna stop it.
I'll kill you all.
It's people like you who are the problem.
And Judgment is the same way!
And anyone who has power! All you ever do is abuse it!
Power? Power, you say?
I'll show ya power.
Ahh!
You fool.
That punch was the least that you deserved.
You use other people's power as
an excuse for your own weakness.
There's almost nothing more pathetic than that.
Don't you realize even the great Railgun,
Ace of Tokiwadai, started out at Level 1.
She didn't become a Level 5 because of some fluke.
She worked hard for it every step of the way.
You know, even if she was a Level 1 instead of a Level 5,
I have a feeling she still would
have been able to get the best of you.
There you are!
Oh! I was so worried about you!
I know. I'm sorry.
But thanks to Misaka, here we are.
All in one piece! See?
The lady from Tokiwadai saved us just in time!
Yeah!
She was pretty amazing, huh?
There's something strange about it, though.
The place where they were standing
is the only spot left unharmed.
I don't know how Sissy's ability could have this effect.
Hey! There she is!
I have to admit, you really
outdid yourself this time, Sissy!
Thank you so much for everything!
Huh?
Oh. Yeah.
I know! Let me be your personal slave
for a day. I'll do anything you want me to!
I could wash your back for you or give you a nice massage.
What is your bidding, Sissy?
I'll pass.
That sounds more like what you want.
Thanks anyway.
Aw, come on!
Just a short massage, then! Please!
I don't deserve the credit.
My railgun wouldn't have made it in time back there.
It wasn't me who saved Uiharu and that little girl.
It was him.
An ambush?
You angry?
Huh?
Everybody seems to think I'm the one who
saved those guys from the graviton explosion.
If you come forward, you'll be a hero.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Everybody got out of it all right.
I don't really see a problem. Do you?
So what difference does it make who saved them?
Stop acting so cool!
Why does he always have to play the hero?
And why does he only do it in front of me?
It's driving me crazy!
It's always the same thing.
That guy really ticks me off!
You should calm down, Sissy. You're turning red.
Next time...
I'm not turning red!
Ooh, bright red!
Your face is burning my eyes!