[Luna giggles]
[Luna] Do you know why
the flowers bloom?
[Dune grunts]
They bloom in order
to make everyone happy...
Because when a flower is
at its most beautiful
it can bring a smile
to anyone's face.
[Dune grunts]
May you have...
eternal healing too.
Are those Luna's flowers...?
Luna's scent?
[Dune]
Finally... My homeland...
Luna!
Dune? Is that you?
[Dune] Miss Luna...
my humblest
apologies for being away
from your side for so long.
[Luna] It's good
to see you again...
The flowers have
welcomed you as well.
Why thank you... our sun.
Come Dune...
Let me grant you
healing and peace.
Our precious and
endearing light...I'm...
...happy... just to see you.
Is this really the city
Luna's supposed to
be staying in...?
Has she saved anyone?
Let's hope.
But... I wonder if
she hurts like the others...
Could Luna be suffering to?
Ohji told me one time...
...that Luna heals the weak
by spilling her own blood...
...and because of that
she can only heal so
many people at a time.
I hope it doesn't hurt her.
[Friender howls]
[stone being moved]
[Crowd]
Luna! Luna!
Luna.
So that's... Luna?
She's so pretty.
Dune.
I can hardly believe he
was able to make it this far.
Yeah.
Is he your friend?
He shares the
same dream with us.
Well if that's the case...
I'm gonna go say hello!
[Ringo laughs]
[Ringo]
Hello!
[Dune]
Casshern?
[Casshern]
I see you made it.
Only because you
allowed me to live...
I wanted to kill you...
...but you were kind
enough to spare me.
So have you... seen Luna?
I have...
May Luna's grace be with you.
Wow, there are so many of them.
You doing all right
down there, Ringo?
I'm doing good.
[Friender growls]
[Refugeebot A] Hurry up! We have
to get him to Luna right away!
Hang in there buddy.
We'll have Luna fix you up
in no time, I promise.
Thank you.
[Casshern] We are truly in
the land of salvation now.
[punching and fighting noises]
[Refugeebot E]
Break him!
[Refugeebot F]
Get him! Get him!!
Oh now you've done it!
[Refugeebot E laughs]
[Refugeebot E] What's wrong?
Is that all you've got?
[Refugeebot G]
Not even close.
[further fighting sounds]
[Refugeebot E]
Yeah!
[Refugeebot F]
Destroy him!
What are they
doing that for?
The fighting never
seems to end...
Even if they're hurt...
...they will be healed.
And does Luna
know about this?
The Sun does
not ever give...
Almost all choose to
take from it selfishly.
So wait...
Are you saying you haven't
accepted her healing yet?
Do you know why
the flowers bloom...?
Perhaps there is
no reason for it.
[punch]
Oh dear... You poor thing...
and after he had met Luna.
I suppose anything is possible.
That's the guy from last night.
[robot henchmen grunt]
[thud]
[Refugeebot D groans]
What the hell's going on?
Oh my gosh... It's so sad!
Hey hold on...!
This one here
is still alive!
He may as well be dead...
He is... beyond my healing.
[Lyuze] This is not at all...
what I had envisioned...
This entire city...
and even Luna.
Wait Ohji.
[Lyuze] I don't know if you
could sense it but Ringo
wants out of here
as soon as possible...
She's tough though...
The little girl's
sticking it out
because she made that
promise to Ohji.
[Casshern thinks]
Luna... What are you?
[footsteps]
[Dune] Luna.
I don't like them.
I don't like to watch
all of them ruin...
So bury them all.
We will sow new
seeds in their place...
After all we'll have
plenty to choose from.
[Casshern]
Dune, what are you doing?
Those flowers are still alive.
They'll wither eventually...
and when that day
comes Luna will be sad.
Yeah but so what?
I don't like to see
Luna when she's sad.
It's bandits...!
They're coming after Luna!
[Dune expresses dismay]
Dune...! Your body
can't handle that!
Bring... Luna... now.
Get her out here!
Who the hell is this guy?
Kill him!
[robot bandits yell]
[fighting sounds, bandits
yelling and metal clanging]
[robot bandit V cries out]
Dune can you hear me... Dune?
[Dune groans]
How's Luna?
She's safe... because of you.
[Dune sighs as he smiles]
Casshern, maybe we should
take him to Luna so
she can heal him.
Our most precious
and endearing light...
I am happy just
to gaze upon her.
[Luna]
Dune! Dune!
Dune. Dune?!
Dune! Dune.
Dune!
Please don't die, Dune!
Luna.
I despise... anything
that reeks of death.
What's wrong with you...?
You know that man
gave up his life for you!
He's beyond healing.
[Dune struggles]
Just tell us the truth.
Who are you?
I am Luna... the one
who bestows healing.
What are you doing,
why are you abandoning him?
I simply continue to do
my work of healing
and nothing more.
Was that really her...?
The one people are
hoping will end the ruin?
I told you so.
[Dune]
The Sun gives nothing...
It's simply the way it is...
Just as the flowers bloom...
Not for anyone's sake...
but their own.
[Casshern]
That's not true!
For all the beings that
inhabit this world...
each and every one
of them lives for something
with every breath they take.
That's the most
important thing...
I've learned on this
journey of mine.
But I am content with...
...just being a flower...
Blooming and withering away.
[Dune]
That's all I ever needed.
[Dune exhales]
Dune!
No!
[gust of wind]
[robot guardian] Hey...
Who are you?
[Braiking Boss groans]
Correct me if I'm wrong
but you look too well off
to be in a graveyard.
Then why are you here?
I am its protector.
[Braiking Boss] Perhaps a friend
of yours is interred here?
Afraid not I just
happened to drift here...
...but after spending some
time with these graves...
...I decided it'd be best if
I stayed until the
world fell into ruin.
And why is that?
It makes me feel better...
knowing that there
are so many who were
destroyed before me.
[robot guardian] From what I can
tell this used to be the site
of a military base...
...operated by a guy
named Braiking Boss...
I've heard these are the
graves of his own men.
[robot guardian] Strange guy,
if you ask me...
I mean why would he
have to dig so many graves?
I know why...
[Braiking Boss] He
probably didn't want to
forget the amount of
lives the ruin claimed.
He wanted their memories
to live on so he carved
the massive loss
of life into his heart.
[robot henchman C]
Lady Leda! I found someone
who claims to know
where Luna's hiding!
[Leda chuckles]
[Casshern]
Luna.
Oh... Hi, Casshern.
All these rumors that
you can heal the sick
are nothing but lies...
From what I've seen
you haven't saved anyone.
It makes no difference
because everyone will
die without me,
giving off a pungent...
deplorable stench.
[Casshern thinks] What I felt
at the end of my journey...
...was neither hope
for the future...
...nor despair for the dead...
But pure anger.
[Casshern] What we found at
the end of our journey
was not truth...
...but an illusion
disguised as hope.
Next time...
The Paradise of Lost Hope.