Who are you?
I am Casshern.
Luna...
I will kill you.
[LYUZE] You say you have
no memory of your sins.
Well then you should be
made to remember them.
Casshern you are
a killing machine.
You see...
You took the life of the
Sun that was named Moon.
And because of that,
the ruin began.
And now...
the world is dead.
This is all your fault!
[CASSHERN] You're saying
that I killed the world?
What have I done?
Tell me.
How could you
forget such a thing?
Huh? It was
so despicable.
[LYUZE] How?
There's no sense
in slaying you now.
Nothing good would come of it.
Killing you at a time
when you don't remember
your own atrocities would,
in a way, be saving you.
And you deserve
so much worse!
No forgiveness...
No, I want you to
witness the devastation
of the ruin you have caused
with your own two eyes.
Even if you are incapable
of feeling pain,
at the very least you'll know
firsthand of the sins
you will die for.
[LYUZE YELLS]
[LYUZE THINKING]
Do you understand?
Well you will, at least
once I'm done with you!
I'm not gonna let you off easy!
Not until you feel
the pain I've felt!
[CASSHERN] My sins...
[BRAIKING BOSS] Something
ominous spread over the world,
sending everything into
a downward spiral...
One needs just look around
to see the results...
Soon after, the planet morphed
into a mass of insanity.
[BRAIKING BOSS LAUGHS]
It's quite sad, actually.
The result of a life-force
void of a conscience...
From then on, forward
progress ceased to exist.
[HOWLING]
[BRAIKING BOSS]
Those responsible for
spreading chaos
throughout the world...
...were the very humans
who created us.
[BRAIKING BOSS LAUGHS]
Oh, I'm sorry, am I
boring you with my story?
[SKULL FACE] It was my
impression that robots can
live forever.
[BRAIKING BOSS]
That's a thing of the past.
[SKULL FACE] We had
dominion over all humanity.
[BRAIKING BOSS]
But not anymore.
[SKULL FACE]
Then why do robots have to die?
Why?!
I don't want to die.
Where 's Casshern?
If we eat him,
we'll live forever!
[BRAIKING BOSS]
That's just a stupid rumor.
[SKULL FACE]
Look.
I was engulfed in
fire and yet I'm fine.
No human is capable of that...
I will not die. I can't die!
[SKULL FACE LAUGHS]
[BRAIKING BOSS] But were we
ever alive to begin with?
[HOWLING]
[WRENCH]
Root, is ruin the only thing
waiting for us in our future?
I can feel your
hand and its warmth
as it cascades up my arm.
That's weird for
a robot to say, right?
Still... my heart flutters
whenever I am with you.
Your touch is laced
with... such electricity.
That a great energy...
is born deep within me.
And the moment
I became one with you...
...I felt as though
I had become human.
Humans are mortal, right?
And after I had fallen
in love with you,
it was as if the
ruin had stopped...
and everything had gone back
to the way it was before.
I want to be with you...
I don't want to be ruined.
[SCRAPING SOUND]
Oh don't worry, we will
be together, sweet Wrench...
...until we succumb to the ruin.
[WRENCH] Root...
[LOUD THUD]
[ROBOT WARRIOR A]
The sight of robots
trying to act like humans...
...makes me want to
smash them into dust!
Die... Die along
with the humans!
Root, hurry up!
Look out!
[TALL ROBOT] Whaddaya say
you play lovebird with me?
LOUD THUD]
[ROOT SCREAMS]
[WRENCH GASPS]
[WRENCH YELLS]
[SHATTERING SOUND]
[ROBOT WARRIOR B] My arm!
[WRENCH] Root!
[ROBOT WARRIOR B]
Look what you did to my arm!
[LOUD THUD]
[RED ROUND ROBOT ROARS]
[WRENCH] Friender!
[CRASHING SOUND]
[METALLIC "PING"]
[WRENCH GASPS]
[ROBOT WARRIOR B YELLS]
[THUD]
Be careful!
[TALL ROBOT YELLS]
[FRIENDER WHIMPERS]
[LOUD THUDS]
[RED ROUND ROBOT ROARS]
[RED ROUND ROBOT YELLS]
[FRIENDER GROWLS]
Stop.
[TALL ROBOT] You haven't begun
to ruin yet... How annoying.
[ROBOT WARRIOR B] Ahh!
[SHATTERING]
[LOUD THUDS]
[RED ROUND ROBOT ROARS]
[TALL ROBOT YELLS]
[RED ROUND ROBOT YELLS]
[METAL SNAPS]
[TALL ROBOT YELLS]
[HIT LANDS]
[CRASHING SOUND]
[SHATTERING]
[LOUD THUD]
[ROOT] Hey uh...
Thank you for
rescuing us.
We will be forever
in your debt.
[ROOT] Even though we know
we'll be ruined eventually,
we'd like to live out
our final days in peace.
[CRACKING AND CRUMBLING]
[CRACKING]
[DOCTOR] I'm afraid Von
just perished from the ruin.
[FRIENDER HOWLS]
Von... I'm so sorry
we weren't with you.
[ROOT]
I hope he knows he's not alone.
[NITA]
Our turn will come soon enough.
[HERMIT ROBOT A]
Yes, soon. Wait for us.
[DREW]
At least Von went peacefully.
[HERMIT ROBOTS] Huh...?
Earlier... we were
being attacked
and this kind
stranger saved us.
[HOWLING]
[CRUMBLING]
[SKULL FACE]
I refuse to die...
I will not let that happen!
I will find this
Casshern and eat him,
and I will live forever!
[DOCTOR] I don't see a single
spot of rust anywhere on you.
It's a miracle you haven't
felt the effects of the ruin.
It's quite strange...
You don't look human,
yet I have a hard time
believing you're a robot too.
You look brand new,
as if you were built
yesterday... very strange.
[CASSHERN] I don't know
what I am, or who I am,
let alone what is happening
to the world around me.
Doctor, will you help me?
Tell me what the ruin is...
Tell me what's
happening to this world.
[DOCTOR] We have neither words
to pray with nor tears to cry.
We are left to just
accept the ruin as it is,
quietly and without dissent.
[SPIKEY HAIR ROBOT]
Thank you Doctor...
I didn't want to be stuck
on my back just yet.
[CASSHERN GASPS]
This is the ruin?
[DOCTOR] Iron oxide has slowly
begun to overwhelm our bodies.
Most no longer accept
spare parts or repairs.
And building new robots
is impossible now.
But why?
I don't know why.
The one thing we do know is
that the ruin is... inescapable.
Are you saying the
ruin can't be stopped?
Yes... but... I heard
something recently...
That we can be saved
if we devour the one
called Casshern...
Though it's probably...
just a silly rumor.
[CLATTERING]
[DOCTOR] I don't believe there's
any reason for the ruin to stop.
[DOCTOR] I felt alive for
the first time in my life
when I realized that
I would fall to ruin.
Because in order to die...
you must have life.
Robots, who were once
considered eternal,
gained a level of humanity
when they obtained death.
We should accept death,
just like humans do.
Everyone who came here
was in agreement
with that philosophy.
Together we will await
our final days peacefully,
until the ruin takes us all...
It shouldn't be much longer.
[NITA THINKING]
Von... May you rest in peace.
[DREW GRUNTS]
[DREW LAUGHS]
[NITA LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[DOCTOR] You should leave
here as soon as possible.
This place doesn't suit you.
[CASSHERN]
Why's that?
[DOCTOR] Because...
you have more life in you
than all of us combined.
Oh, what's wrong Friender?
Does Wrench not want to play?
I'm afraid we can't give
you the attention you deserve.
[LYUZE]
This is all your fault!
[WRENCH]
I heard you're leaving.
The ruin doesn't seem to have
any effect at all on Friender.
And if he stays with us
he'll be all by himself soon.
Would you be willing to take
Friender along with you?
Well I...
Cause you see...
He's a lot like you.
He's always very tense.
He doesn't seem
to understand himself.
You two are so alike,
maybe you could--
[ROOT] Wrench!
I thought you may've had
a change of heart and left.
We both agreed...
...we would stay here and
meet our ruin peacefully...
...now didn't we?
Aren't you two afraid of dying?
[ROOT]
Not if we're together...
I know you must
find it quite odd
for two robots like
us to be in love,
but it's the real thing.
It's strange but it's us.
[ROOT] Friender, keep us
company awhile longer, okay?
[DREW] Twenty-one...
Twenty-two... Twenty-three...
Twenty-four...
Twenty-five...
[DREW LAUGHS]
[CROWD LAUGHS]
[DREW] Twenty-eight...
Twenty-nine... Thirty...
Thirty-one...
[NITA] He's good.
[DREW] Thirty--
[DREW GRUNTS]
Well... I'll be inside,
awaiting the end in peace.
[DREW YELLS]
Drew!
[SHATTERING SOUND]
[NITA]
I'm so scared...
I don't... wanna... die.
[NITA CRIES]
[WRENCH SOBS]
It'll be alright...
I'm not gonna
leave your side.
[CASSHERN THINKING]
If this is my fault,
then what should I do about it?
[NITA] No!
[SKULL FACE] Casshern!
[NITA GASPS]
[WRENCH] Nita!
[SKULL FACE] Casshern,
I'm going to devour you!
[NITA YELLS FEARFULLY]
[SKULL FACE ROARS]
[DOCTOR]
Stop! Don't do it!
Put her down!
You have the wrong robot!
Please... Trust me.
She isn't Casshern.
[WRENCH GASPS]
[SKULL FACE]
There you are!
[WRENCH GASPS]
[SKULL FACE] Casshern!
[ROOT YELLS]
[WRENCH SCREAMS]
No, Root!
[SKULL FACE]
I'll devour you!
[SKULL FACE YELLS]
[FRIENDER WHIMPERS]
Friender!
[WRENCH]
Stop it! Please!
[SKULL FACE]
Out of my way!
[FRIENDER WHIMPERS]
[WRENCH SCREAMS]
[SKULL FACE] Casshern...
I've been told that if
I eat you, the ruin will stop.
That's why I'm gonna
devour you and live forever!
[SKULL FACE ROARS]
[SKULL FACE]
Who the hell was that?!
I am... the one
you're looking for.
[DOCTOR] I knew it.
Casshern.
[SKULL FACE LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[SKULL FACE]
Casshern... I know the truth!
I can devour you
and avoid the ruin!
You can't stop me!
[SKULL FACE YELLS]
[SKULL FACE] There's no sense
in avoiding the inevitable.
I will devour you!
[WRENCH] I'll be right
here... until the end.
[CRUMBLING]
[CASSHERN GRUNTS]
[EXPLOSION]
[SKULL FACE MUMBLES
INCOHERENTLY]
[DOCTOR]
My hunch was correct.
You really are Casshern.
Now please...
Leave this place immediately.
[ROOT] Doctor, that's
a terrible thing to say.
Casshern just saved us.
Why would you want--
[DOCTOR] Root!
You know... you could
save us all again Casshern.
[CASSHERN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[ROOT]
Save us from the ruin.
But... how?
[ROOT GRUNTS]
Well, we'll survive
if we eat you!
Root, no.
[NITA]
I want to live...
I don't want to die.
I want to live.
[HERMIT ROBOTS MURMUR]
[WRENCH]
Root, stop it!
What about our promise?!
We agreed to
accept the ruin... right?
Yes, we did. But we
found a way to avoid it...
I'd rather not die.
No!
Stop now.
[ROOT GRUNTS]
[CLATTERING]
I don't want to die...
I want to live.
[HERMIT ROBOTS MURMUR]
[HERMIT ROBOT B]
Kill Casshern! Devour Casshern!
Kill Casshern!
[HERMIT ROBOT C]
Devour Casshern!
[SHATTERING SOUND]
[WRENCH GASPS]
[WRENCH] Friender!
[METALLIC CRASH]
[CASSHERN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[WRENCH]
I thought we could be human.
I believed the two of
us were connected...
We felt emotions that
were new to us,
inside our hearts
and our bodies...
That way facing the
ruin wasn't so scary...
We thought we could be human.
[CASSHERN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
But... why...?
You said we'd welcome ruin...
You said we would
get through it together.
[CRUMBLING]
[WRENCH]
None of this would've happened
if you hadn't come here!
We would've accepted our fate,
but you showed up without
a trace of rust on you!
[CASSHERN YELLS]
You really are immortal.
No!
[FRIENDER WHIMPERS]
Stop... Stop...
Just let it be!
[CASSHERN] Robots who
believed in eternal life
continue to perish.
But not me...
♪ closing song ♪
[CASSHERN]
There was a human being...
...wandering alone,
on a decaying Earth.
Next time...
To the Ends of Agony.