[Young Lyuze crying]
We must protect her.
We must protect her?
We must protect her...!
[Young Liza and young Lyuze]
We must protect her!
[flowing water and clicks]
[slicing metal and
fighting sounds]
Lately... I've been having
a lot of vivid dreams.
[Lyuze yells]
Over and over again!
[metal slicing]
[thud]
Always... the same as
the last one before it.
[robot creaking upward]
[slicing and impact]
Lyuze... You must kill Casshern.
[Lyuze gasps]
[walking in puddles of water]
[metal disintegrating]
I am... it's just...
[metal disintegrating and
collapsing into water]
No.
[Young Lyuze cries]
We must protect her.
We must protect her?
We must protect her...!
[Young Liza and young Lyuze]
We must protect her!
[Young Liza] You and me
need to watch over Luna and
protect her forever and ever...
Without us she could be hurt,
and no one wants that.
We... must protect her.
Lyuze... You have
to kill Casshern.
I have to kill Casshern...?
Why Liza?
[Young Liza]
Finished!
Behold it's Luna!
[Young Lyuze laughs]
[tide rolls in]
[wind softly humming]
What are you staring at...?
Do you believe I can't
accomplish anything...?
Do you pity me?
[Lyuze] You killed the
Sun named Moon...
...and brought the world
to the brink of ruin.
But that's not all...
You led my sister
Liza to her death and yet...
I can't kill you?
[Casshern grunts as he attacks]
[Lyuze] I will kill
you as vengeance
for taking away my sister!
[metal slicing through metal]
[Lyuze gasps]
[Lyuze]
Liza!
Is this a dream too...?
It's time to wake up.
[Lyuze gasps as she is stabbed]
[soft guitar music]
[Lyuze thinks]
Casshern's hand...
...pierced through my chest.
[Lyuze thinks]
It feels like it's burning...
Is that just his body heat...
coursing through me?
[Lyuze thinks]
What is this I'm... feeling?
Don't wake up.
[Lyuze thinks] Casshern...
He is a danger to this world...
...and all its inhabitants.
[Lyuze thinks]
He murdered Luna...
He murdered my own sister.
[Lyuze thinks] Casshern...
is an enemy to the world.
[Lyuze thinks] I knew
what it was I had to do.
[Lyuze thinks]
I was sure I knew, and yet...
...I just had to
get it over with.
[Liza] Yes... Casshern killed
someone who we both held dear...
So why...
I know Liza...
It's the truth.
I know all too well...
I know all too well.
[basketball bursts]
[Lyuze gasps]
You're my sworn enemy...
What the hell were
you thinking that day...?
Who is it you
think you are, huh...?
That it...?
You're just gonna keep
staring at me like that?
[Lyuze thinks] You are the
target of my vengeance...
I've survived so many years...
...just to get the
chance to kill you...
I've even outlasted the ruin...
So why do I continue to...
Why can't I...?
[cracking]
[water drips and echoes]
[Lyuze thinks]
Casshern is a killing machine...
...the embodiment of insanity...
Unsatisfied with killing
the Sun named Moon...
you spread death and
destruction throughout this
collapsing world...
...unaware of the pain
and suffering it caused.
[impact blasts and thuds]
You're the lowest
form of life in existence.
And yet.
[glass bottle rolling on brick]
[Lyuze thinks] And yet you
know nothing at all...
Not even who you were.
[Lyuze thinks] Nor did you know
how the world got this way...
You didn't even know
you had killed Luna.
[glass bottle rolling on brick]
[Lyuze thinks] And yet you
know nothing at all...
Not even who you were.
[Lyuze thinks] Nor did you know
how the world got this way...
You didn't know
you had killed Luna.
[Lyuze thinks] Even the fact
you're immortal escaped you.
[glass bottle rolling on brick]
[Lyuze gasps]
[wind begins to howl]
Myself with... Casshern?
[Lyuze]
Casshern.
Hey baby...
You shouldn't be peeking
in on other's peoples destinies.
[Lyuze]
Who are you?
Oo Baby, I'm just here
to grant your wish, that's all.
I don't want to have
anything to do with you...
Now take off.
[Molester]
Ooh, I like 'em feisty.
I can grant wishes
beyond your wildest dreams.
But what is... my wish?
[Lyuze sighs]
[slicing into skin and splatter]
What was that...?
What am I doing?
So that's the
blood humans... shed.
[Lyuze]
If I were human...
...would I grasp these
complex emotions?
[Lyuze thinks]
I'm in love with Casshern.
These are my... sins.
I can't... see anything.
[Young Liza]
Who am I?
[Young Lyuze] I know...!
You're Liza!
Hey, how did you know that?
[Young Lyuze] How? Because
you're the only one here!
[Young Lyuze giggles]
[thunder rolls]
Oh no!
Hey Liza...! Liza!
Where are you?
[Liza]
You think... you worry...
...you grieve...
[Liza] Yet through all that
you're able to create your
own path, are you not... Lyuze?
Liza... Is that you?
[Liza] I have sinned in my life,
and that has led you astray.
[Liza] Though in hindsight,
maybe that was a good thing...
After all, it did
lead you to Casshern.
[Young Lyuze struggles]
[Young Lyuze]
Liza, wait up!
[robot bandits]
Kill Casshern...
Devour Casshern.
[battle cries and
fighting sounds]
[Lyuze thinks] If Casshern
struggles in the ruin...
Then so... shall I.
[Lyuze] If Casshern
desires to find Luna...
...I shall seek her too!
[robot bandit cries out]
[shattering]
[metal slicing through metal]
[thud]
So... if Casshern
has eternal life...
[Lyuze thinks] Then
I shall stand beside him
until my last own demise.
♪ insert song ♪
[Lyuze] Will I also
succumb... to the ruin?
Hey Liza!
[Young Lyuze laughs]
Wait, is that me?
[Lyuze reacts with concern]
[Young Lyuze laughs]
Nothing fazes you.
I won't be discouraged.
[Young Lyuze laughs]
Goodbye Liza.
[Casshern] The truth that lies
deep within one's heart...
...shall one day reappear
and turn to madness.
[Casshern]
Next time...
Believe in the Flower
that Lives in Your Heart.