[rain shower]
[Lyuze thinks]
Casshern's eternity...
...is my ruin.
[Lyuze thinks]
The wind... so dry...
The world is dying
little by little...
...like a sand dune...
slowly eroding in the breeze...
Luna... are you out there...?
Will you really save us?
[ground breaks]
[Ringo emits sound of surprise]
[ground crackles]
[ground cracks]
This ground's unstable.
[Ringo]
Casshern! Lyuze...!
Come quick look!
Look look look!
Over there...
I think I found it...
You know the castle!
[explosive projectile]
[impact]
[ratcheting sound
and rocks falling]
[metal pulled taut]
[impact]
Hmm...
[Casshern cries out]
[Helene chuckles to herself]
Who are you?
[impact]
[metal creaking]
[impact explosion]
Casshern!
[Helene lightly chuckles]
[fighting]
[ground crackles then snaps]
[swords colliding and grunts]
[Lyuze grimaces
as she struggles]
[swords scraping]
[Lyuze cries out
as she is kicked]
[Lyuze coughs in pain and
struggles to breath]
[Helene laughs]
[Helene]
How pathetic...
There isn't any value
in fighting you at all.
The only reason you've made
it this far is because
of him, right...?
In other words you're
incapable of
protecting yourself...
Oh you poor little thing.
[Lyuze screams]
[swords collide]
[Lyuze struggles]
[Lyuze choking]
I will end your suffering.
[explosion]
Casshern!
Death will be
upon you soon...
But don't worry,
your man will be
right behind you.
[Lyuze choking]
[Helene]
Now... die!
[metal colliding]
[metal clanging on ground]
[Castor cries out]
[twisting metal]
Castor no!
[Castor cries out]
[Helene shocked]
[Helene]
Castor!
[water dribbling]
[Ringo emits a shocked sound]
It's alright... did you see
something scary Ringo?
One time...
...Ohji told me a story...
it's scary...?
He said there's all sorts
of spooky monsters
living inside caves.
[Lyuze]
It's okay...
We're here with you.
[Lyuze] So... What else
did Ohji tell you...?
Anything specific?
[Ringo]
Huh?
[Lyuze] Such as...
What kind of monster it was?
[Ringo]
Umm... He said it was
a snake monster
called a Hydra...
It had nine heads and
you could get rid of
eight of them but the
one in the middle...
the very last head
was indestructible...
so you couldn't kill it.
[Ringo] No matter which head
you cut off and how
many times you did it...
...a new head would keep
growing in its place...
...making the Hydra
stronger and stronger.
[Lyuze]
Wow... That's amazing.
[Ringo]
Doesn't it sound scary?
[Lyuze]
I'm jealous...
[Ringo]
Huh?
[Lyuze] Jealous
of its life force...
Instead of decaying over time,
it becomes more powerful.
[howling wind]
[splash]
[Lyuze thinks] Someday
my body will rot away...
...and turn into rust...
Will it be a slow agony,
or instantaneous?
[Lyuze thinks]
Back when all I thought
about was exacting my
revenge on Casshern...
...the ruin wasn't even
an issue with me...
So... why do I feel
this way now?
[metal ding]
[Ringo laughs]
What is this place...?
It's gorgeous.
[Casshern]
I can't believe it.
[Casshern] I'm shocked a
place like this can still exist.
Standing here it's
almost as if...
...the ruin never even happened.
Yeah I know.
[footstep]
Here 'ya go.
[Ringo strains as
she stretches up]
Maybe there's a fairy
with lots of feathers
here instead of a
monster with nine heads!
[Ringo]
Casshern...!
Let's go this way!
[Lyuze gasps]
[Lyuze gasps and panics]
[wind howls]
[Ringo gasps]
[Ringo]
Lyuze!
[rain hitting the ground]
[Casshern]
Lyuze.
[Casshern] Let's rest... You
shouldn't overexert yourself.
I'm fine...
We're not too far
from Luna's castle now...
so let's keep moving.
[Lyuze gasps]
[Casshern] No... We'll
wait here until the rain stops.
Why are you doing this...?
Is it for my sake?
[Lyuze]
Because my ruin will
get worse if I'm exposed
to the rain for too long?
And In this cold rain...
my body's more susceptible...
I could simply drop
dead at any moment...
You've noticed it, haven't you?
[Casshern]
Lyuze.
Take it easy...
I'm just a little worried about
your well-being, that's all.
You can't understand
what it's like... Casshern...
You are so beautiful.
Just like the monster
Ringo mentioned before...
You're invincible... I'm not.
[Lyuze thinks] I don't know
what I should do at this point.
[Lyuze thinks] Luna...
If I go to your castle
and you're not there...
...will that mean there's
no salvation left for me?
[Lyuze] The rain...
it's not stopping.
[Lyuze gasps]
[creaking metal]
[Lyuze shudders]
[metal ding]
[metal ding and echo]
Come on what's
wrong with you...?
Just fight me already.
I'm confused...
Why are you doing this?
Tell me the truth...
...do I have any
worth as a fighter?
[Lyuze] That woman told
me I'm pathetic...
Said I couldn't protect myself.
What am I...? Nothing?
[Lyuze] Am I just another
one of the walking dead,
incapable of taking a stand...?
I mean, here I am with these
strong feelings for you...
But will I not...
...make it long enough to
see where this all goes?
Just fight me...!
Break me apart...
Destroy me.
At the very least...
...you can release me...
...from my suffering.
[blade impacting
into Casshern's hand]
[Casshern] You wouldn't believe
me if I told you how many times
I've thought the same thing.
[Casshern]
Let's go find Luna...
What do you say?
We may not be able to
reverse the damage that's
already been done...
...but we... will find
a way for you to live.
But the question is...
do I want to live?
I do want to.
[impact]
I will not die.
You again.
[Helene struggles and gasps]
[thud]
[Lyuze struggles to breathe]
I won't die!
I don't want to die.
Nor do I...
I'll live...
[glass shattering]
[Lyuze] Even if there
is no meaning or value.
Let's go...
[Lyuze]
We have lives to live.
[Casshern] When we
attain that which we seek...
...it becomes a brief illusion
before disappearing
into nothing.
Next time...
For Whom Do
the Flowers Bloom?