[Ringo] It's not your
fault Casshern...!
It's not your fault...!
It's not...
Casshern.
[Robot refugee A] My hands...
they're falling apart.
[Robot refugee A]
I just need to be patient...
...because Luna will
stop the ruin...
I just need to believe,
and it will end.
[Robot refugee A]
Look... Look...!
The ruin, it stopped...
It's over!
[Robot refugee A] There's not a
single speck of rust on me!
[Robot refugee A] Anyone
who isn't ready to die...
...go to Luna!
[robot refugees
murmur to each other]
[Robot refugee A] Go to Luna
and accept her healing!
So Luna is alive...?
How can that be?
The healing...
What kind of relief
could there be
in this world?
[baby girl emits a small cry]
[Lyuze] Are you still
looking for Luna?
[Casshern]
Yes.
You're wasting your time.
It's just a rumor...
Your actions lead to
the death of Luna,
which caused the suffering
you're witnessing right now.
[Lyuze] I'm willing to bet that
you believe your sins will
be forgotten if
you find her alive.
That won't happen...
...because she's dead.
Tell me... Wouldn't you rather
have Luna be found alive?
[Lyuze gasps]
[Lyuze] There's
no simple answer.
But if she is...
...then what did my
sister die for...?
Then... why've I been
seeking revenge...?
For nothing?
I'm going to see Luna now.
We'll see what
happens... afterwards.
[metal slamming into the ground]
[Robot warrior A]
Death to all deserters!
[Robot warrior B]This is
what you get for spouting
such nonsense that Luna
will stop the ruin...
It's a lie!
[Robot warrior C] Lord Dio is
the only one worth believing in!
[Leda]
Luna is alive.
[Dio] Eventually...
We shall grant healing
to robots and humans...
Just as Luna had done before.
True...
but when Luna did that...
...there was no ruin
to contend with.
[Dio] Back then... I never once
stopped to consider why
Braiking Boss wanted Luna
assassinated so desperately.
Yes but...
...it's important that
you understand something.
[Leda] There can
only be... one victor.
Luna, huh?
Ohji... who is Luna...?
It's all everyone's
talking about out there.
If they're talking about
her it's probably just a
crazy person claiming
to be someone else...
...or just a phantom.
[Ohji] There's no chance they're
talking about the real Luna.
[Ohji thinks] Casshern
killed Luna...
Damn him.
[Ringo]
Ohji.
Smile for me...
Like this!
[Ohji emits a laughing grunt]
[Ringo chuckles]
[Ohji sighs]
[Ohji] You must be
getting sleepy, Ringo...
What do you say we
take a break here soon?
[Lyuze]
Say you do find Luna,
and every question
you have is answered.
[Lyuze]You'll quickly
discover it's no different from
what I've told you myself...
Doesn't that frighten you?
[Casshern] The old me
probably would have been...
...but not now.
[Casshern] I've seen the
ruin with my own eyes...
...and I am
determined to stop it.
[rolls of thunder]
[Casshern] Careful...
The ground is loose over there.
[ground crumbles]
[Casshern] I've seen the
ruin with my own eyes...
...and I am
determined to stop it.
And to do that...
I need to find out
exactly what happened.
But even if Luna
does turn out to be alive...
...it doesn't change the
fact that the ruin is
still your fault...
That will never change.
[Ohji] What luck... Getting
a flat in the middle of nowhere
while it's raining.
Ohji... are you alright?
[Ohji] I'll be
done soon.
[Ringo laughs]
[Ringo]
Yay, rain!
[Ringo continues to laugh]
Ringo...! You're getting wet...!
Get back inside the truck!
It's okay, I'll be fine...!
I love the rain, Ohji...!
Whenever it rains it
looks like the whole
world is sparkling...!
More than anything
I love the sound it makes.
[rain drops land in puddles
of water and metal]
[raindrop hits object]
[raindrops hit bottle
causing musical tones]
[Ringo]
What's that?
It's so pretty.
[Ringo laughs]
[Ringo] I know!
[Ringo]
I can see so far away!
[Ringo] Look at me
I have super eyes!
It's Casshern...!
I can see Casshern!
[Ohji] Ringo!
Let's get going!
[Ringo] Ohji...!
Casshern's over here!
Casshern is where?
Down that cliff...!
Casshern!
Ringo, wait!
[Ringo] Come up
and look, Ohji!
Oh dammit...
Don't think I like the
looks of those storm clouds.
[Ringo]
Casshern!
Cassh--
Ringo...?
Why are you here?
[Ringo chuckles]
I just tripped.
[Casshern] Ringo,
are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine...
[Ringo]
Check it out!
Don't you think
it's the prettiest...?
I found it all by myself!
[Lyuze] Ringo,
what's going on...?
Look at you,
you're soaking wet.
[Ringo]
I'm okay.
No, you're not okay...
You aren't even
wearing a coat,
what'll you do if
you start rusting?
What to do?
[Lyuze] We need to get her
somewhere dry, and fast.
Maybe... you should get
closer to the fire.
[Ringo giggles]
Come on...
Stay still for me.
'Kay!
[Ringo continues to laugh]
Ringo...
Her ruin is spreading.
Alright... put your arms up.
'Kay!
Ringo?
Are you... bleeding?
Uh... looks like it...
...but it doesn't
hurt though... I'm fine!
[Lyuze] But...
you're starting to rust.
You're dry now...
put your clothes back on...
Don't want you gettin' cold.
[Ringo]
Okay!
[Ringo] You go on first,
mister shirt...
[Ringo emits an anxious sound]
[bottle rolls across floor]
[Rain pouring and
thunder crashing]
[water pours in]
[thunder cracks]
I don't mean to intrude...
Hope you don't mind
if I escape from the
rain for a while.
[Braiking Boss] My
decaying body and water
don't get along too well.
[thunder cracks]
Ooh, feels nice and cold!
[Ringo]
Hey Lyuze!
Come look... over here!
[fire crackles]
Why are you looking
at him like that?
You haven't taken your eyes
off Casshern since you got here.
Is that right?
Are you searching
for Luna as well?
[Braiking Boss grunts]
[Lyuze] It may not really
be her, you know.
[Braiking Boss]
Why's that?
Because.
Because...?
Because Casshern killed her?
What...? How do you know that?
[Ringo] The only way to make
these shells look prettier...
is to put them... in the water.
[Ringo] It worked!
They're sparkling!
The only way to find
out if this Luna is
real or not... would be by
meeting her face to face.
[Braiking Boss] Same goes
for her healing powers.
[Lyuze]
Casshern.
No... it couldn't be?
[Braiking Boss lightly chuckles]
[Casshern]
No... your...
[Ringo emits a cry
after stumbling]
[bottle breaks]
[Casshern]
No... it's...!
Braiking Boss!
[Casshern groans and
begins to struggle]
[Lyuze]
Casshern?
[Casshern]
Luna... Luna...!
[Braiking Boss] Seems like
your memory is coming back.
You were bound to
find out sooner or later...
Now you can take
responsibility for what
you've done to this planet...
Isn't that right, Professor?
What are you saying?
Professor...?
Then you're...
That's correct...
Standing right behind me...
Casshern... is your creator.
Oh well...
Way back...
A long time ago a
robot tried to become God...
No wait... He did something
even dumber than that...
He tried to create God.
[Braiking Boss] It was an
attempt to gain eternal life,
all though we'd already
conquered that ages before.
[Braiking Boss] Even humans had
attained it thanks to advances
in modern medicine,
leaving only the unluckiest
of humans to perish.
But there was one advantage
humanity held over
the heads of robots.
[Braiking Boss]
The ability to procreate.
If we could reproduce,
it would be our final step
towards surpassing mankind...
We could become Gods.
You're crazy...
It's impossible.
But procreation
is possible in theory.
The systems installed
in their bodies were
fundamentally different
from your standard robot.
[Ohji] You have males,
who can create new
cells within their bodies...
And females, who are
capable of accepting those cells
to fertilize their own...
creating a new,
complete life form.
[Ohji] I'm referring, of course,
to Casshern, Dio and Leda.
So does that explain
why Casshern is immortal?
[Ohji] No... I had
nothing to do with that.
[Ohji]
And in the end,
all three were
deemed failures.
[Ohji]
After much debate...
...their only use was found
in exploiting their
abnormally powerful bodies...
they became killing machines.
Killing... machines.
[screams of victims]
[Casshern]
Is that all I am...?
A monster of death?
[Ohji] I have no idea how
you became immortal...
It must have happened sometime
after you killed Luna.
[Braiking Boss]
You're right...
It was Luna...
perhaps it all began
after her first death...
and her subsequent
reappearance...
Luna.
She was the Sun
that was named Moon...
That was her identity.
[Braiking Boss] Eventually
the masses began
to tire of eternal life...
but she came along
and reinvigorated that desire,
giving us the strength to live.
That's what Luna was about.
[Braiking Boss]
However, the fact remains
that only one is capable
of ruling the world.
[Braiking Boss] There's
no need for two suns...
That is why I gave the order...
[Braiking Boss]
For you to kill Luna.
[Casshern screams]
[Thunder cracks]
[Casshern]
Kill... Luna.
Casshern wait!
[Casshern struggles]
[Casshern]
Kill...
...Luna.
Casshern?
[Ringo]
It's gonna be alright.
Kill Luna.
Kill her...
Oh Casshern...
You're not a bad person.
[Casshern]
Must kill!
[Casshern screams]
Luna!
[thud]
[Casshern]
Kill... Kill...
[Casshern continues to struggle]
Casshern...! Stop!
[Ringo]
I don't want you to die!
[Casshern]
K-Kill...
[Ringo]
No...! Don't do it...!
Don't!
[Ringo] It's not
your fault, Casshern...!
It's not your fault...!
You're a good person...!
I know that...! Please, don't!
[Ringo] Stop... If you keep
doing that, you'll die.
Please stop...
I don't want you to die...!
Please Casshern!
[Ringo screams out of the
last word] No... No... NO!!!
♪ closing song ♪
[Casshern] Those incapable
of escaping their past...
...can only move forward
by embracing the truth.
[Casshern]
Next time...
The Truth Illuminates
the Darkness.