[Ringo in cries out in pain]
[Ringo]
Casshern!
Casshern.
[Ringo cries out]
Lyuze?
I've decided to go.
You have?
I'll be fine...
[Lyuze grimaces]
[Ringo]
Lyuze, I'm sorry...!
I ran off and now you're hurt...
[Lyuze] I'm alright...
How are you doing?
[Ringo]
I'm fine.
Ringo.
Casshern.
We now have Luna
in our hands... finally...
Soon the ruin will be over.
Why are we not giving
healing to everyone?
[Leda] What would be the point
if everyone were the same...?
Beauty exists because there
are so many who aren't.
Because...
...if you are not envied...
...how can one experience
the value of beauty?
Those with...
the gift of beauty...
...will identify us as the
ones who granted it to them.
[Leda] I take it you
don't understand?
No matter you can
do whatever you please.
[Leda] Let us go
to Luna... together.
There is much to be done,
like us gaining eternal life.
[Dio]
I don't want it.
[Leda]
You don't want it...?
What do you mean...?
Even you are showing
signs of ruin!
So you've gone from
being a boy to a man...
I must admit that makes
me... a little bit sad.
[Leda]
Very well...
though you will
change your mind...
You'll have to find a
way to stop your decay.
[Leda]
And then... I will...
[drop of water in pool]
[Luna] I was
starting to wonder
why no one had
come in for awhile...
Shall I perform
the healing here?
From here on out
your healing will be
reserved for only
the chosen ones.
I won't allow you to
stop the ruin on
your own anymore.
Why's that?
Because I said so, that's why.
[Leda]
I suppose you believe
saving everyone is
part of your destiny,
but unfortunately...
you're going to
have to stop...
And if you defy me...
[Luna]
I don't mind that.
[Luna] All I do is eliminate the
death that is put before me.
So... we have an understanding.
And you?
Sorry?
Answer me this...
Are you one of
these chosen few?
[Luna cries out]
Luna... You are done
playing queen... so...
...now I will be the one
granting or denying healing,
only I will do it through you.
[Luna]
If that's what you want.
Gaining eternal life...
you lust for it don't you?
Now come.
Luna... Give me your blood.
And now... my ruin
will finally come to an end.
[Leda]
I... no longer see death.
[Leda chuckles]
[chains rattle]
[Casshern grimaces in pain]
[robot henchman A]
He's been trying to heal
himself for hours...
Though his chances of
a perfect recovery are slim.
[Dio]
He will.
[robot henchman A]
Huh?
You better recover, Casshern...
So that you may stand
before me once again...
And if you don't
then I swear I'll...
[Casshern wails in pain]
[Dio]
Recover... and fight me!
[Ringo]
Come on, Ohji...!
We have to save him!
I already told you.
He'll be fine!
But you saw Casshern, Ohji,
he was suffering and in pain...
So much pain.
[Lyuze]
It's okay.
[Ringo]
Casshern.
[Lyuze]
We'll save him I promise.
[impact]
There's no end to it.
[robot guardian]
Yeah.
[Braiking Boss]
It's why the one who
dug these graves ended
up running away.
And why I had to take over.
It's certainly not
for my health.
You know you
could always run.
No, I can't...
That would be akin to
giving in to the ruin.
[robot guardian]
But don't get me wrong...
I don't think the guy who
ran off lost by doing that...
We all have different things
we must do in our lives.
[robot guardian]
Different priorities.
You don't say... huh.
It's over...
The ruin has stopped.
[Leda]
It's beautiful...!
I now hold the world
in the palm of my hand.
[Leda] Soon I will move to an
entirely new level of being.
That of never ending life.
Dio you have to see!
[Leda]
My ruin. It's stopped...!
I feel like my old self again...
Light as a feather!
Dio, it's time you
stopped your ruin as well...
Once you do
everything will change...
You won't be worried
about Casshern anymore.
[Dio] Don't you dare
raise a finger at him.
But the problem
is he's in our way...
The only one's who should
have immortal bodies
are you and I,
Surely... crushing his
head should be enough.
[Dio] I'll be the one
to defeat Casshern.
Wait... Have you seen him...?
He's already defeated...!
Don't you realize?
You've already beat him.
No... You don't decide that.
[Leda]
Listen... I feel like
my entire body is
brimming with life!
Dio... You and I...
We can do what no
robot's ever done before.
[Leda] We have the
ability to create life!
Leda... do you really
still desire that?
[Leda]
Dio... We can become Gods.
There is only one thing
I desire in this life.
And that is to fight
and defeat Casshern.
Now wait.
I'm leaving the castle.
You're doing what?
You can stay here
and fulfill your dreams...
I'll be taking on Casshern.
[Leda]
And what if I say no...?
Anything out of my
control is an impediment...!
I will not stand for it!
Don't become an obstacle.
Are you saying you're
willing to kill me?
Whether you live or die
is entirely up to you.
It's been so long...
...that we've been together...
I never imagined it would
end with us at each
other's throats, like this.
[shattering]
[Leda lets out a shocked gasp]
[Leda]
Why...?
I thought I was healed!
Here's an idea...
Go back and have
her heal you again...
...as many times as you need.
Don't walk away from me!
Wait...? What is Dio
doing with Casshern?
Luna... Can you explain this?
I thought the ruin
was supposed to disappear!
Oh... Well maybe
the healing I gave
you wasn't strong enough...
However, rest assured that
this will have absolutely
no bearing on
your eternal life...
So don't worry.
Eternal life's meaningless
if I'm not perfect...
If I'm not beautiful.
[Luna]
But you are beautiful.
[Leda]
I know what's going on.
You don't want anyone
else to have your beauty.
And that explains why
you didn't fully
heal me before.
You said the healing
wasn't strong enough...
If that is the case then...
I want more of it...
...your blood.
I've no problem with that...
But be warned,
it will be painful for you.
I don't care about that...
I can handle it!
[Luna grunts and blood splashes]
[Leda sighs]
It's coming...
Soon I will
obtain everything...
great power...
Pure beauty... Endless life.
[Casshern cries out in pain]
Why me?
I'm not saving
you from death...
I merely kept you alive
so that I could fight you...
...without interruption.
Now do whatever you
have to do to get back
to the shape you
were in before.
But I... can't...
...not anymore.
[Casshern bellows in pain]
Endure it...
You owe me that much, Casshern.
For I'm only alive
to fight you!
I was able to survive...
...and now it's your
turn to do the same.
[Luna] Perhaps I went
a little too far this time...
...but still, there's
no need to worry.
[Leda moans in agony]
Isn't eternal life
just so beautiful...?
To think I have the power
to make people live.
[Luna]
I will not kill them...
...like the old me would have.
[Leda moans in agony]
It's so very wonderful.
[Leda moans and
then screams in agony]
[Casshern wails in agony]
[thunder]
[Casshern] The rain...
has it stopped.
Yes.
Dio... why are you doing this.
Quit you're yapping
and heal yourself.
Why do you want to fight...?
I don't see any reason for it.
Well, there is a reason...
...but you wouldn't
understand...
...you see you've always
been one step ahead
of me our entire lives.
[Dio] But now, the reason
why is meaningless.
The only thing I desire
is to defeat you...
...and that...is all...
This single obsession... allowed
me to survive until recently.
[piece of Dio falls in water]
Have you not
been healed by Luna?
Why not?
[Dio] I believed if
I gained eternal life...
...this feeling of starvation
would fade away eventually...
...granting me inner peace.
But if I can battle you
just once then I'll
forget about the ruin...
Fight me...
It's the only reason
I have to exist.
You know what...?
You're no different than
the robots and humans
I've come across.
They all lived hard lives...
...to the fullest...
They have more life
in them than those
healed by Luna...
...including myself.
And you are the same...
It's a mystery to me
why you'd think that
when you're ruining away.
[Dio]
I don't understand.
Well I'm not sure I do either...
I don't understand
the idea of immortality...
Same goes for... all the joys...
...and the fears
of life and death...
I don't get it...!
I never will!
Casshern...! If there is a
such a thing as a joy in life,
then fighting you is the
only joy that exists in mine!
Fighting me?
Now Casshern... Fight me.
[explosion]
[Casshern and Dio
wail as they fight]
[Dio thinks]
This is it...
I could never replicate this
feeling by living forever...
Now...
[Casshern]
I can feel it...
This is Dio's...
[Casshern]
In the face of death...
I learn about
the meaning of life.
Next time...
Those Who Return.