If I am slain here today...
the world will be led into ruin.
That does not concern me...
My task is a simple one,
to take your life just as
I was ordered... Die... Luna.
[CASSHERN GRIMACES
AND BUILDS TO A ROAR]
What... did you say?
It's because...
you are... Casshern.
Casshern?
Yes.
[DIO] One who cannot
contain himself in battle...
[DIO] One who cannot feel peace
until every living
thing is destroyed...
It all stems from
who you are, Casshern.
Casshern.
Casshern
You were created...
...to take every
lifeform on this planet
and turn it to dust.
For that purpose?
You are different...
...from robots and humans.
Who are you?
How do you know
details of my life?
[CASSHERN] What else
do you know about me?
[DIO]
What else?
Try everything there
is to know... about you.
But see...
all that doesn't matter.
Because you are going
to die here today.
By my own hand.
[METAL FOOT POUNDS THE GROUND]
[ROBOT BANDIT 1] Not if I have
anything to say about it!
[ROBOT 0]
Bandits!
[ROBOT K]
They're still here?
[ROBOT G]
Oh no!
[OHJI]
Don't worry!
It looks to me like
they're after Casshern.
Be careful!
[CASSHERN SURPRISED]
[ROBOT 0]
That guy is Casshern
[ROBOT BANDIT 1]
Casshern is ours.
[ROBOT BANDIT 2]
He's our prey
and there's nothing
you can do about it!
Their prey?
[METAL STEPS POUND THE GROUND]
[METALLIC LAUGH]
[ROBOT BANDIT YELLS]
[COLLISION AND FALL]
[ROBOT GROWL]
Friender.
[ROBOT BANDIT 4]
Don't get in our way.
You can't stop us!
[METAL ON METAL CRUSHING]
[RINGO REACTS SHOCKED]
[VARIOUS METALS
COLLIDING DURING FIGHT]
[DIO CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Oh wow... he's...
he's as strong as Casshern.
Of course I am.
Casshern and I both
share nearly identical
power profiles.
But the only thing is...
...you don't know
how to use them.
[DIO] With this power,
you could dominate
everything on this planet.
Just like...
...Braiking Boss did before.
So I will become the dominator
and I will be unstoppable.
I will...
change this world forever.
Braiking Boss...? Is that?
You honestly don't remember...?
Not even me?!
Ohji?
You mean to tell me
you've even
forgotten our destiny?
Too bad...
I remember it clearly.
I don't... remember a thing...
Nothing about this world...
...let alone what kind of
involvement I may
have had with it.
Well... I guess can help you
with some of the grey areas...
If you want.
[DIO] Humans were no
match for robots...
[DIO] They wiped humanity
off the planet
and took their place of reign
by becoming the new
rulers of the world.
And the one in control...
...was Braiking Boss.
But then...
...everything was led
to ruin after the death of Luna!
Ruin.
[DIO] We could do nothing
to stop its progress.
But... I now have the
ability to stop the ruin.
[RINGO AND OHJI
REACT SHOCKED]
[ROBOT R] You can
really end the ruin?
[ROBOT J]
Is that true?
The absolute truth...
See once I have attained
world domination, I will be
capable of granting the
robotic race with eternal
life once again.
[GROUP SIGHS WITH AWE]
Eternal... life?
[DIO]
But in order to do that...
...I must kill you.
Now...
In exchange for your life
every being in this
world will be saved...
Casshern!
Hold on.
In exchange for my life?
[ROBOT M]
The ruin!
[CLANKING METAL
AND GHOSTLY MURMURS]
[RINGO REACTS SCARED]
[ROBOT M]
You can stop the ruin?
[ROBOT R]
We don't have to die?
[ROBOT G] So if Casshern dies...
then all of us will be saved?
Casshern.
Please save us.
You have to.
[ROBOT I]
Please... save us.
[ROBOT K]
You have to do it!
[RINGO SHUDDERS IN FEAR]
Please, save us.
[ROBOTS GROAN AND PLEAD]
[ROBOT M]
Save us.
Hear that... Casshern?
Every one of them
is in search of salvation.
If your life were to end
not only would those
standing around us,
but every living robotic
creature suffering from
the ruin would
be saved from death.
You were created in order
to annihilate all life yet
you can redeem yourself
by sacrificing your own...
Doesn't that sound wonderful?
[CASSHERN]
So...
If I die...
...the world will be saved?
Not exactly, I have to kill you
to discover the mechanisms
that govern your life
for it to work.
Really... why's that?
You are the one who killed
Luna and began the ruin...
...yet you don't show a
single sign of it anywhere
on your body.
So If I can
discover your secret...
...then the world will be saved.
[CASSHERN]
My secret?
I'd like to know
the secret... for myself.
I want to know
why I can't die.
What makes me immortal?
But if what you say is true,
and you can indeed kill me,
then it doesn't really
matter in the end.
Casshern.
[OHJI SIGHS UNDER HIS BREATH]
Now...
You said that you and
I have identical powers.
Maybe crossing paths with you...
...is exactly what
I've been waiting for.
Okay... Please kill me.
Casshern!
You don't have to ask.
That's why I'm here.
[LEDA CHUCKLES]
[IMPACT EXPLOSION]
[FRIENDER SNARLS]
Friender!
So Casshern... It seems wherever
you go you always find conflict.
[BLAST]
Please... Just end it.
[DIO GRIMACES]
[MASSIVE BLAST]
[ROCK AND DEBRIS HIT THE GROUND]
[EXPLOSION]
[DIO]
What the?
Damn you!
[BLAST]
[DIO]
I cannot lose to you...
[DIO] Because I am the one
who will change the world...
Now die!
I won't let you...
kill Casshern.
[LEDA CHUCKLES]
Who was that?
Well.
Now's your chance to
avenge your sister's death.
Don't misunderstand me...
It's not like I don't
despise you anymore...
...the next time our paths
cross I will kill you...
...but it will be
a fair fight cause
the last thing I want to do
is embarrass my sister's memory.
[LYUZE] Until then you do not
have my permission to die,
[CASSHERN GRIMACES IN PAIN]
Casshern?
[CASSHERN CONTINUES
TO GRIMACE IN PAIN]
[DIO GRIMACES IN PAIN]
[LEDA]
Dio.
[WIND BLOWS AND CLOCKS TICK]
[LEDA SIGHS]
[RINGO]
Are you awake now?
[CASSHERN]
Am I... alive?
Friender's doing a
lot better too.
Friender?
[RINGO] That is his name,
right...? The doggy?
Alright... now you're set boy.
Thank goodness Ohji
was able to fix you doggy.
Ohji... so you saved me?
I didn't lay a finger on ya...
Your body seemed to
find a way to heal your
wounds on it's own.
You're amazing.
[RINGO]
That must have something
to do with why you're
always so pretty looking,
Always... on my own.
Why can't I just die?
The man I fought.
Do you know what
happened to him?
A strange looking lady
with long hair took him away.
I see... I remember now.
[CASSHERN] He said the world
could be saved if I died...
He said he would discover
the secret of my body
and why the ruin
doesn't affect me.
And if that happens...
I can die... and finally
atone for killing Luna.
[OHJI]
Alright, that's enough.
Let's go.
What about him?
We'll surely be attacked again
if we're caught near him...
We don't have enough
lives to spare for that.
[CASSHERN] Do you know
anything about me?
I can't be hurt...
Why is that?
I have no idea... but...
from the rumors I've heard,
Luna was also immortal.
You did the impossible...
...killing someone
who could not die...
For all I know she may
have placed a curse on you.
[CAR STARTING UP AND MOVING]
The impossible... No way.
Luna... was immortal too.
[CASSHERN THINKS]
I have nothing to go off of...
...but I still want to know...
What was Luna...?
And what am I?
[CLOSING SONG]
[CASSHERN] There was a woman
who built a tower...
...saying "the world
still has beauty."
[CASSHERN]
Next time,
The Woman of the Tall Tower.