[gentle breeze]
[Luna gasps]
Do you smell it...?
These flowers reek of death.
[Casshern] Luna. The idea
that you have the power of
healing is a lie...
You haven't saved anyone...
...not even your own guardian.
Where are you going...?
I thought you came here
seeking salvation from me.
[Ringo near tears]
There's no need
for sorrow anymore...
Contrary to what you believe,
I can save you from the ruin.
How do we know that it's true?
[Casshern] These
thousands of people...
Can you really heal them?
[Luna] A single drop of
blood from my veins...
revives the soul completely...
and grants eternal life.
I have answered the calls
of those who have come here...
...and I have granted
all their wishes.
A single drop of
blood from my veins...
revives the soul
completely...
...and grants eternal life.
[Luna] I have answered the calls
of those who have come here...
And I have granted
every one of their wishes.
But then... what about Dune?
Why would you...
allow him to die?
[Luna] Dune refused my blood,
and as a consequence...
...he went the way of ruin...
Ideally... Death is a concept
that should not exist.
[Casshern]
Not exist...?
What do you mean?
Death is terror... darkness...
The fact remains...
If people could escape
the pits of death and ruin...
...they would all
be much happier...
Only then could they...
...thoroughly enjoy
the bounties of life.
You're wrong.
[Casshern]
If that's true...
...then explain to me this...
Why do I suffer so much?
Hold on, wait a second...
Are you saying everything
I'm doing for these
people is wrong?
[Luna] Stopping the
ruin is a bad thing?
Truth is...
I want you to stay.
What for?
So he can take Dune's place...
...and protect this
field of flowers.
[Lyuze]
Let's go Ringo.
Wait!
[gust of wind]
[Dio] My body
is decaying, Leda...
And yet, as my skin rusts
and movements dull,
my senses are more
acute than ever before.
[Dio] They're
sharp, and exacting.
As I continue...
...to hunt down Casshern
in the void of darkness...
Endlessly.
Lets be going...
Luna awaits us.
Just you wait, Luna...
I'm going to make you mine.
Are you coming...?
It's time to go...
We already dug a
grave for Dune...
There's no reason
for us to stay here.
But Lyuze...?
No... It's okay.
I don't want any
part of her... salvation.
[Ringo groans]
[Lyuze] Oh no!
[Casshern] Ringo!
I'm alright... Let's go...
I don't...
I wanna leave.
Is this yours?
[robot boy A]
Mmm.
[robot boy utters
questioning grunt]
[robot boy A laughs]
[robot boy B yells]
[clank]
[robot boy B laughs]
[robot boy B yells]
[clank]
[robot boy B laughs]
[crowd laughing]
[crowd groans]
Luna's clinic is just up ahead,
that is if you're interested.
You'd better hurry and
get your place in line...
...before that
thing turns to rust...
Come on back after
you receive her...
grand healing...
Well...? Go on.
Yeah we'll do that.
[robot boy B yells]
[clank]
[Ringo groans]
What was that...?
Those people were so strange...
...they all hated us
for no reason!
There's a shadow of
death following us...
That's why they
don't like us.
Does it have anything
to do with them
escaping the ruin?
It does...
That town there...
it's for those who've been
touched by Luna and
will live forever.
[Lyuze]
You know, it's funny...
...for so long I hoped I could
someday escape the ruin...
And yet I...
despise that town.
[Casshern] In the morning we
should go see Luna again.
[Lyuze expresses shock]
It is the reason why
we came all this way.
[Lyuze]
But...
Is...what Luna
said really true...?
Is bowing down before her
and begging for salvation
our only option?
Do you have the resolve...
...to accept your fate
just like Dune did before?
[metal pings]
I see what you mean.
[Lyuze] I'm sorry... I just...
don't know what to do.
[Lyuze] You can feel it,
can't you...?
The rust is starting to
spread on my skin...
It's rough to the touch...
My lips too.
I wish I could...
...be smooth like you
and not have to worry
about rusting... But...
[shattering]
[Lyuze] If I went back to
that town to be healed...
I feel like... like it would
change who I am inside.
And I don't want that...
I want to stay who I am.
Lyuze... It's okay....
[Ringo] You know I can
walk by myself, Casshern.
Hey, are you listening...?
Come on, put me down!
Woah careful!
Now be a good girl.
[Friender whines]
Ringo it's me!
Ohji?!
Thank goodness I found you!
Ohji you're here!
[Ringo]
Ohji!
Are you alright...?
Please tell me you
haven't seen Luna yet.
Sure I did. I met her.
[Ohji] Huh?
But I... only met
her, that's all...
She didn't heal me.
It's not salvation after all.
What Luna really
grants people...
...is death.
[robot refugee A]
Luna...!
Luna, please. I beg of you.
Grant me salvation...!
It is my... only hope.
[robot refugee A]
Save me!
[Ohji]
Many years ago,
the world was filled
with eternal life forms...
Humans found the secret
to living forever and
quickly adopted it,
straying far away from death...
Braiking Boss found the
idea to be wrong,
so he used his great power
to exterminate the human race.
[Ohji]
A sliver of humanity
survived his holocaust
under the protection of Luna...
...albeit just barely...
Soon after robots began
to flock towards Luna,
worshipping her much
as the humans did...
Seeing this as a hindrance
to his plans of
world domination...
Braiking Boss ordered
her assassination...
Unbeknownst to him,
Luna did not offer
her followers salvation...
...but instead
the gift of death.
Death?
In a world overflowing
with immortal lifeforms...
...she gave a natural
lifespan back to all beings.
Lifespan?
She believes that true life...
...can only be experienced
when there is death.
Hold on...
From what we've seen
over the last few days,
Luna is stopping the ruin.
[robot refugee A utters a
shaky emotional sound]
[robot refugee A]
Thank you, Luna, thank you...
You've saved me!
[Ohji sighs]
Well maybe... but...
According to the research
I've done lately...
the Luna of old...
You're saying the new Luna
and the one from the past
have different motives?
Do you know why?
Well perhaps in the
interim between her
first death and resurgence...
...something changed.
Well... Here I was rushing
to stop Ringo from being
saved by Luna when...
[low rumble]
[crowd laughing and talking]
[Ohji thinks] So this is the
product of Luna's healing?
Here we come... Miss Luna.
[marching sounds in distance]
[Ohji] So if we
meet with Luna...
...the ruin will
really stop...?
Ringo...
[Ringo whimpers]
Let's go.
[Ringo]
Ohji.
[Ohji]
Come on, Ringo...
Let's go see her so
we can have her fix you...
I don't want you to suffer.
No way...! I can't.
Why not?
Luna does stop the ruin but...
It's wrong...
Like the sun never setting.
[Casshern]
It's unnatural...
A distortion of reality.
[Casshern] I think Ringo
is sensitive to that...
...and she doesn't like it.
[Ohji]
You may be right...
A world without
ruin would be...
...strange and abnormal.
But still...
...it's an alternative to dying.
[Ohji] Those who have accepted
Luna's healing have survived...
...and yes, their lives
may never be the same.
[Ohji] But I do not want
Ringo to suffer and die...
Is that so wrong?
[Ringo whimpers]
Now... Ringo... Come on.
[Ringo grunts disapproval]
Ohji... That's enough.
[Ohji] Lyuze...
You're coming with us...
Or would you rather die?
[Ringo struggles]
No, Ohji, I don't want to!
Please, let go of my hand!
Ohji... Stop it.
Casshern...
Are you going to fight me?
[robot bandits yell]
Casshern.
He's in the way.
[Ohji] So Casshern,
are you going to fight...?
If you don't believe in
the concept of survival...
...then what's the
point in fighting...?
It's easy for you to speak
nobly when you're immortal.
[robot bandits yell]
[robot bandit wails]
[Ohji] You don't know
what pain feels like...
What the fear of death
can do to one's mind.
[Ohji]
Don't you see, Casshern...?
You're the only one with
the luxury of immortality!
Casshern wait!
What the hell are you doing?
Casshern.
[fighting and
robot bandits yelling]
[Casshern cries out]
[Dio thinks] Look at him.
He's breaking.
[Casshern thinks]
The feeling of pain...
The fear of death.
No!!
[Dio] Casshern,
so beautiful and immortal...
Your life is perfect...
Why throw it away?
[Ringo]
Casshern.
[impact]
[Casshern thinks] The sun's so
bright... unnaturally bright.
[impact]
[Lyuze screams]
Casshern!!
[Casshern] Those who
seek it, fear death...
Those who do not,
experience life.
Next time...
A Drop Called Eternity.