Who are you?
I am Casshern.
Luna... I will kill you.
[WHOOSH]
[LOUD THUDS]
[METAL WARRIOR YELLS]
[SHATTERING SOUND]
[BRAIKING BOSS] It all began
on one day... the ruin.
From the moment
he murdered Luna,
our world began to crumble,
and there is nothing
we can do to stop it.
[BRAIKING BOSS LAUGHS]
[RUMBLING]
[EXPLOSION]
The one responsible for
her death is Casshern.
Yes, that damned Casshern!
He owes the world a favor
after what he did to it.
[METAL WARRIORS]
Kill Casshern...
Kill Casshern... Kill Casshern.
Kill Casshern! Kill Casshern!
[CASSHERN GRUNTS]
[CASSHERN YELLS]
[METAL WARRIOR YELLS]
[CASSHERN GRUNTS]
[CRACK]
[LYUZE] The one who brought
ruin to this world is named...
...Casshern.
[METAL WARRIOR YELLS]
[LOUD THUDS]
[METAL WARRIOR H]
Devour Casshern!
[METAL WARRIOR YELLS]
[METAL WARRIOR H] Kill...
[LOUD THUD]
Kill Casshern.
Devour Casshern!
What for...?
How does eating me serve you?
[METAL WARRIOR H LAUGHS]
[METAL WARRIOR H]
The ruin will never stop.
My body couldn't last another
six months in this
state of decay...
...even if you let me
walk away unharmed.
And what does that
have to do with me?
[METAL WARRIOR H] Casshern...
If I eat you, I will
attain eternal life.
You're lying!
[METAL WARRIOR H] I have no idea
whether it's true or not, but...
I'm not going to sit around
waiting to die without
trying something!
You better believe that!
Die!
[CASSHERN YELLS]
[PUNCHES LANDING]
The ruin won't stop...
They believe if they eat me
they will live forever.
[WHOOSH]
[THUD]
[LYUZE] Kill Casshern...
Devour Casshern.
Kill Casshern...
Destroy Casshern.
[CRUMBLING SOUND]
[LYUZE LAUGHS]
[LYUZE]
They seem to be quite frail
once they've lost
their consciousness.
It's such a fragile world...
full of robots...
[CASSHERN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[CASSHERN YELLS IN PAIN]
[OHJI] Huh...?
Ohji...
Ringo?
What are you awake for?
Why don't you try
to go back to sleep?
[RINGO GIGGLES]
[TRUCK STARTS]
[METAL WARRIOR C]
Devour Casshern.
[BRAIKING BOSS] Pinning
your hopes on a rumor...
What could eating
him actually do?
It would never be
enough to stop the ruin.
[METAL WARRIOR C]
You... You're that...
[POWERING DOWN]
[SHATTERING]
Yes, the end has
already begun...
But don't forget you are
still obliged to make...
...amends, Casshern.
As are we.
[OHJI THINKING] So Casshern...
You've finally awakened.
[BRAIKING BOSS]
We knew this would happen.
Looks like business is
about to pick up for you.
[RINGO LAUGHS]
Pretty.
Who me?
[RINGO]
Mm-Hmm.
Mister, are you human?
So you're a robot?
Well... probably.
You're not sure?
What's a human?
[RINGO]
I don't know.
I haven't seen very many before.
But... I thought you may
be one of those humans...
...'cause you're so pretty.
What's your
name mister?
You have a name,
don't you?
My name?
My name... is Ringo.
My name is Ringo!
I am...
[METAL WARRIORS]
Kill Casshern...
Kill Casshern... Kill Casshern.
[CASSHERN GRUNTS]
I am Casshern.
Casshern?
[RINGO] Aww...!
Hey, I was arranging those!
You're mean...
Mister... Water!
Huh...?
[RINGO GASPS]
[RINGO GIGGLES]
[RINGO GRUNTS]
[RINGO LAUGHS]
[RINGO GIGGLES]
Are you... a robot too?
[RINGO LAUGHS]
I had started to rust real bad,
but Ohji fixed me right up.
If it weren't for all
that rust earlier,
I bet I'd be much prettier.
But now... the ruin has begun.
So, what is the ruin?
Is it happening to me?
Ooohhh!
I don't get it!
All I know is you're
really pretty, Mister.
You're not all broken down
and corroded like me.
You're more like a human!
Well, I better get home...
...before Ohji starts
worrying about me.
♪ Ohji is a worry wart!
Sweet Ohji is a worry wart! ♪
Bye-bye!
[RINGO LAUGHS]
Wait, hold on!
I don't think
you're broken at all.
I think you're beautiful.
Here you can have this...
Of all the shells
I've found so far,
this one's the prettiest.
It's for good luck.
[CASSHERN] Thank you.
No, thank you.
[CASSHERN GASPS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[RINGO LAUGHS]
[CASSHERN] Was that...
...Luna?
[CLATTERING]
Ringo!
[RINGO GASPS]
[WHOOSHING]
[METAL WARRIOR I GROWLS]
[METAL WARRIOR I]
Humans deserve to feel the ruin,
just like us!
But Ringo is a robot.
[METAL WARRIOR I]
A robotic brat? I hate brats!
I can't stand
their foul stench!
Uhh...
[CLATTERING]
[METAL WARRIOR I] The world
is heading towards ruin.
There will be no
place for brats like you.
Now die.
[CRACKING]
[LOUD THUDS]
[METAL WARRIOR I GRUNTS]
[CASSHERN YELLS]
[METAL WARRIOR I YELLS]
Let her go... Walk away.
[METAL WARRIOR I]
Who do you think you are?
Drop her.
[METAL WARRIOR I]
Wait... Are you...?
Ringo.
So pretty... Heh.
Hey there, Mister.
[RINGO LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[LOUD FOOTSTEPS]
[METAL WARRIOR I]
Now I know who you are...
You're Casshern!
I hear that if I eat you,
it will stop the ruin
from advancing...
I don't believe for
a second that it's true.
But I do understand why others
would want to
believe such a lie.
I've never seen such a new
body before... so pristine.
It won't be for much longer...
not after I crush it!
What the... What was that?!
[METAL WARRIOR I YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[METAL WARRIOR I SCREAMS]
Careful Mister.
[METAL WARRIOR I]
Stop, please!
No, wait.
[METAL WARRIOR I YELLS]
[METAL WARRIOR I SCREAMS]
[CLATTERING]
[METAL WARRIOR I]
I don't want to die.
[CRUMBLING]
Huh...
[TRUCK APPROACHING]
Ohji!
[CLATTERING]
[OHJI]
Please stay where you are.
Seeing you...
I can hardly believe it.
[RINGO CRIES]
[TRUCK STARTS]
[CRUMBLING SOUND]
[LYUZE] She's upset because she
doesn't want to leave your side.
As I thought...
Your true nature has
come to light today.
The ease at which you
kill is impressive... yet...
...you're the worst thing
to happen to this world.
You're despicable.
You know about me...?
Please tell me.
I know enough about you
to want to kill you for it.
Then come
out with it...
Just what am I?
Casshern...
You are a killing machine.
You see...
You took the life of the
Sun that was named Moon...
...and because of that,
the ruin began.
[CRUMBLING SOUND]
And now...
the world... is dead.
[CLATTERING]
[CASSHERN THINKING]
I know nothing...
...not even myself...
Yet my enemies
call me... Casshern.
[CASSHERN]
There was a commune of robots
who accepted
death as their fate.
Next time...
A World Replete
with Death Throes.