[Nico laughs]
[impact blast]
[lazy breeze]
[Nico giggles]
[Nico blows a petal away]
Bye bye petal!
[water flowing]
[impact and metal shattering]
[robot bandit a]
Who cares about Luna...?
No one even knows
where she is...
She's a phantom!
[heavy thud]
[robot bandit a]
We'd put our trust in Dio...
...before her... any day!
[robot bandit b]
Joining the army doesn't
guarantee your survival.
[robot bandit a] Your priority
should be finding Luna!!
[Bolton]
Devour Casshern!
[Bolton] The only way to
obtain eternal life is to
devour Casshern!
Don't do it!
[Bloton] Attack!
Devour Casshern!
[robot bandits bellow in unison]
[heavy footfalls]
[Bolton]
Die Casshern!
Devour Casshern!
Where am I?
[Casshern grimaces]
[Casshern] I wonder who
put this flower here.
[breeze blows through]
[metal moving and thud]
[Bolton]
Damn it!
[Bolton] Why do I have
to go through this...?
I am not gonna die...
I'm gonna join the army...
...and survive,
no matter what it takes.
[Bolton utters grunts of pain]
[Bolton] I don't want
to die out here...
...not like them.
[Bolton shouting]
Not in such a barren,
depressing place like this!
[Nico]
Huh?
[Nico lightly giggles]
[Bolton lightly grunts]
[Bolton]
Who the hell are you?
[Bolton] Are you
making fun of me brat?!
[Nico utters a gasp of surprise]
[Nico]
Here... a flower.
Pretty huh?
[Bolton shouts] I don't
want your damn flower!
[Bolton]
Now go!
[Bolton] Get outta my
face you little pain!
[Nico utters a questioning
noise and then laughs]
[Nico]
This one's for you.
I hope you like it.
So tell me...
What are you doing
here anyway?
[Nico giggles]
[Nico sighs and giggles]
[Nico]
♪ La la la-la, la la... ♪
[Nico giggles]
[Casshern thinks]
Is this girl... human?
No... she must be robotic.
[Nico]
Oh no!
Your leg... it's hurt.
[Casshern]
It's nothing... I'll be fine.
[Nico]
Huh?
Don't worry...
I'll heal on my own...
I always do...
for some reason.
But wait!
[Nico] You can't
just leave it be!
Now it's better...
It won't hurt.
[Bolton grunts in pain
as he struggles]
[Bolton continues to struggle]
[Nico grunts as she
moves heavy metal part]
[Nico softly laughs]
[Bolton] Look kid, a wrap isn't
going to fix anything.
[Bolton]
Besides, you just stuck an
arm on me where the
leg's supposed to go, you idiot!
[Nico laughs]
[Bolton fakes laughter]
[Bolton]
You think it's funny, huh?
[Casshern] Why is that girl
going around helping everyone?
[Casshern]
Treating my wound...
...as well as that robot's.
Why is that?
[Ohji]
Her brain's circuitry
is fried beyond repair.
Casshern...! Of all places...
...why are you here?
[Casshern]
I saw a group of robots
trying to push one
of their own off a cliff,
so I tried to stop it.
[Ohji]
Is that right?
[Ohji] I guess those rumors
panned out after all.
[Casshern]
What rumors?
[Ohji] This valley
we're standing in
has been dubbed
the Grave of Robots
for many years now.
[Ohji] After the ruin
began claiming lives,
dead robots were brought
here to be dumped
into mass graves.
[Ohji] I heard that many
were left here while they
were still alive,
so I wanted to come
see it for myself.
So then... that girl was...
I don't know if she was
dumped here or not,
but whatever the case,
she's been here a long time.
[Ohji] From the first moment
[Nico giggles]
I came across her she
struck me as being odd.
[Bolton]
Just stop it already!
[Bolton] I don't care how
many times you do that,
it's not going to
fix my arm! Got it?!
[Impact crash]
[Nico winces]
[Nico]
Oh no!
You alright...?
Are you alright?
Not to worry...
You're in good hands.
[Nico]
Are you in pain?
Thank goodness...
You're not hurt!
[Ohji] She's done this over
and over for years now...
These dolls and decrepit robots
being her only company...
It's really quite sad.
But Ohji...
She seems really happy to me!
[Nico giggles]
[Casshern] She's done the
same thing for so very long.
Because of... the ruin.
[Ringo laughs]
[Ohji]
Huh?
[Ringo]
These flowers...
They're so pretty!
[Ringo]
Did you grow them yourself?
And do you give the
flowers to all the others?
[Ringo]
I love it!
Thank you!
Finished...!
Here'ya go!
[Ringo and Nico giggle]
[Bolton grunts]
[Bolton]
Not you again...!
Don't tell me you're gonna...
Ah... do whatever you want.
[Nico whispers]
She said it looks
really good on you...
Makes you look like royalty!
[Bolton]
Really...
[Ringo giggles]
[Ringo] Casshern...!
Come here and look at this...!
Nico, you too!
Up there. Check it out...!
I put a flower on his head...
Looks like a crown, doesn't it?
[Ringo] Instead of a robot
he's now a prince!
No, no!
You don't think
he could be a prince?
[Ringo] Do you think he's
better than a prince?
[Nico mumbles affirmatively]
[Ringo]
Well maybe he's a queen?
[feet landing]
Hey there!
Hey to you... What's going on?
[Nico laughs]
Nico... What are you
doing here?
Here... it's for you.
Why thank you.
[Casshern]
Lyuze.
Do you know that girl?
[Lyuze] Nico, she's a robot
who looked after Luna.
Luna?
Were you left here...?
Tell me... Have you been here
ever since Luna died?
[Nico giggles]
Stop laughing and
answer me!
[Nico tears up
and begins to cry]
[Casshern]
Lyuze, she can't do it...
Her brain's circuitry is bad.
[Nico continues to cry]
Let's go pick flowers.
Nico... She was with
Luna during her final days.
She also looked
after my sister.
[Lyuze]
She ended up here
because you went
and killed Luna!
[Bolton]
Killed Luna...?
When did this happen?
It was a very long time ago...
[Lyuze] Her death is what
triggered the ruin.
[Bolton] If that's true...
then the stories
must have been lies.
[Bolton]
There was a rumor...
...about a woman named Luna...
She had the power
to give life...
...to robots and humans alike.
That's impossible...!
Luna's not
alive anymore.
[Bolton] Well,
that doesn't change
the fact there was a
lot of us who believed it...
Some of my own comrades did.
[Bolton] We knew we
didn't have long to live,
because of the ruin.
[Bloton]
I guess most of them
just wanted to believe
the rumor was true.
[Bolton] But you can't
blame them for it...
They thought Luna would make
the ruin stop if they met her.
[Bolton] But don't you
think it's a better move
to join Dio's army,
rather than desperately looking
for a woman who
no one knows about,
let alone where she is,
or if she's even alive?!
[Bolton]
Am I wrong?
The thing is...
[Bolton yelps and
crashes to the ground]
[Bolton] Damn it!
Get this thing off me!
[metal creaking]
[Bolton] Look at me!
I'm miserable!
[Bolton] I can't even move
around on my own anymore!
[Bolton]
I feel like a damned turtle...!
Go ahead and laugh!
Mock the cripple...!
I know I look like a moron!
[Bolton] What's the point of
me being alive anymore?
[Bolton] I might as well just
sit here and wait for the ruin!
[Nico expresses
surprise then giggles]
[Ringo and Nico laugh]
[Ringo and Nico
continue to laugh]
[mirror shatters]
[Robot bandit D]
Well what do we have here...?
A couple of snotty brats!
[Robot bandit D]
You'll look cuter under my fist!
[collision and
electronic dog growls]
[Robot bandit D] What the
hell is this damn thing!
[Friender growls]
[Robot bandit D] Bastard...
You're dead!
No...! Casshern?!
[metal shattering]
[explosion]
[Nico quietly stammering]
[Ringo]
Nico.
[Nico]
Oh no!
[Ringo]
What's the matter?
Nico... Where are you going?!
[Multiple heavy footsteps]
[Nico] It's alright...
Don't be scared.
[Nico]
There's no need to cry.
Don't be afraid...
I promise
I'll always be here.
[heavy clanking footsteps]
Stop it!
[Bolton]
What is she doing...?
Damn it... not now!
[Robot bandit F]
Out of my way...
Don't make me hurt you!
[Robot bandit F] Do you really
want to die that badly?
[Bolton]
No...! Don't do it!
[punch thrown]
[Nico cries out]
[Bolton]
Nico!
[body thudding]
[Bolton]
Nico.
[Robot bandit F]
Not dead yet huh?
Lu... na...
Luna... Luna.
[Bolton] You're
gonna pay for that.
[Robot bandit F]
Move aside gimp.
[Bolton]
Nico... stay behind me.
[Robot bandit F]
You were warned!
[Bolton cries out]
[Robot bandit F]
Die!
[metal creaking as Bolton and
Robot bandit F struggle]
[Robot bandit F]
Let go!
[Nico]
Luna... Luna.
[Lyuze]
I don't believe it...
She still cares
about the doll.
[Casshern] I'll take
you there... to see Luna.
Lu...na.
[Casshern] You'll be with
her soon... no matter what.
That much I promise you.
[Nico]
Your bandage...
...it's coming off.
[Nico]
Let me fix it for you...
Here... I'll make it...
just right.
[Nico]
The... ban--
[Nico exhales her final breath]
[Casshern]
Nico.
[Ringo cries]
[Casshern wails]
[Bolton]
As you can see...
...there is no chance
of me moving from here...
I will sit and wait for
you to return... with Luna.
[Casshern]
What is your name?
[Bolton]
It's Bolton.
[Casshern] Well I
promise you, Bolton...
I will bring her back.
[Casshern]
If the world is spiraling
into ruin because of
my own actions...
...then it is my responsibility
to try and stop it from
destroying everything...
If I can find Luna...
...then maybe I can discover
what exactly is needed
to stop this plague.
[Bolton weeps]
♪ closing song ♪
[Casshern] There was a man
who spent his life
protecting one person...
...only to find
out he had failed.
[Casshern]
Next time...
The Man Entrapped by the Past.