[Luna] Casshern...
your blood has changed me.
[metal clanks]
[robot bandit A] Up there.
Is that the place where
Dio is supposed to be?
[robot bandit B] Yeah.
Apparently potential recruits
into his army are
trickling in bit by bit.
[robot bandit A] You think
that guy is wanting to
join up with Dio too?
[robot bandit C]
Him? No way.
Dio?
[robot bandit C]
Is this guy for real?
[robot bandit B]
What a joke.
[robot bandit A] Look at him...
Dio would eat this one alive.
[robot bandit B]
I refuse to be associated
with this rusted
pile of circuits.
[robot bandit C]
I could take you out
right now if I wanted to.
[robot bandit C] Where do
you think you're going?!
[multiple blades slicing metal]
Luna.
[Leda] And after I went
out of my way to fix it
up all nice and new.
[Dio]
Leda.
I don't... want it...
I told you.
I know... but still,
fact remain is you'll eventually
stand above all robotic life.
[Leda] You can't do that
with a broken body.
[Dio] I'd look...
identical to him.
Try to force it
on me once again
and I'll break them both off.
[Leda scoffs quietly]
[Leda]
Dio.
Your wound has already healed.
Your youthful body
is in excellent form.
You... are absolute perfection.
[Leda]
Dio?
Someday...
I myself will ruin...
Do you still think I'm perfect?
Someday...? That may as well
be a millennium from now.
In these times most
individuals possess a fear
of sudden and inescapable death.
[Leda lightly chuckles]
Except... the one
and only Casshern.
[Dio tenses]
[Leda]
Casshern... is special.
[Dio grimaces]
[Leda] Casshern...
he was the
one who made
it to Luna then.
[Dio angrily grunts]
He's the one
who killed her...
...and as a result...
...he was the one who
gained eternal life.
[shattering rock]
[Dio breathes heavy]
[Leda]
Dio.
You have the ability to
become greater than
Casshern ever was.
It is your... destiny.
[Leda] Robots of all walks
of life have amassed
here in response to your call...
That is your army down there.
[Leda] It's time you stood
before them and declared...
...that you intend to create
a new robotic empire.
The same as Braiking
Boss did before.
It will...
surpass all other empires.
[Dio reacts surprised]
What they seek is not
an empire but eternal life
which can only be
granted by Casshern...
...and not by me.
My partner has acquired
another bad habit...
How unfortunate.
[Leda]
However... Dio...
We've come too far
to stop now.
[Leda] If you only knew what
a wonderful symbol you
would make for the Robot Empire.
Eternal life and an empire...
Both of them will be mine.
[wind blows]
But you are no
longer alive...
Why is that...? Luna?
[Luna]
For you and all the
hard work you
do every day.
[Luna]
Thank you.
Luna.
[robot bandit E]
Move it!
[robot bandit E] We traveled for
weeks just to be stood up...?
We've been out here
all day and he hasn't
even shown his face!
[robot bandit F] Was all this
talk of an army a lie...?
I'm not sure he's even
serious about defeating
Casshern and stopping the ruin.
[robot bandit E] If this bastard
Dio doesn't hurry we'll all be
ruined before it even begins!
[metal clanking as
robot bandits fight]
[metal clanks]
[Dune grimaces as
he tries to stand up]
Luna!
[Dune] Luna passed away...
[Dune bellows]
WHY?!!
[robot bandit E]
You!
Silence!
[robot bandit F] We're already
irritated as it is...
Your whining
isn't helping things!
Why... Luna?
[robot bandit E] Are you
hard of hearing? Huh?!
[metal slicing]
[Dune grimaces angrily]
[robot bandit H] What the
hell'd you do that for?
Sweet Luna.
[Leda thinks]
That's Dune...
Luna's personal guard.
[robot bandit I] Luna? The girl
who was murdered ages ago?
[robot bandit J] I've heard
rumors that she's still alive.
Luna.
[Dio thinks] So...
it was him after all.
[Dio thinks]
How pathetic...
Ensnared in the past
and still incapable of
overcoming it...
What a disgrace.
[metal being dragged]
Luna!
Just like...
my own... self.
[Dio] No... The one I should be
focused on destroying is...
[Dune cries out]
[robots bellow]
[metal being sliced]
My my Dune...
You haven't changed.
It was said that Luna
employed the God of Death
as her protection,
and that he was
feared by all.
Disliked by friends
and colleagues...
...he watched over
Luna from afar...
...Dune the God of Death.
There wasn't one
living soul who wanted
to get close to you.
[Leda] It's obvious you still
possess your strength...
...and for that reason I
would love for you
to join us... but that
doesn't seem feasible.
[Leda] You've lost your sanity
over the years, haven't you...?
Allow me to facilitate...
your eventual ruin right now.
[blades colliding]
Luna is DEAD!
[Dune]
Why...? Tell me why!
[Leda]
Dio!
[Dune]
Why... Luna?
Dune... You are no longer
the God of Death...
...but a mere phantom.
Dio... Your body
hasn't fully healed!
Yes... but don't worry Leda.
[Dio] I'll finish him off
along with the past
he can't forget.
Why?
[Dio] Luna's death
was necessary...
In order for robots
to rule over the world.
I know you.
[Dune]
Yes... You're...
You killed... Luna.
I'm right... You're the
one who killed her!
Damn you... Casshern!
Casshern...! You'll die
where you stand...
...for I'm the God of Death!
Dio.
[Dio]
You're no different.
[Dio] All you see when
you look at me is Casshern.
[Dio]
I am not him!
[Dune cries out]
Hold on!
Casshern!
Dio...! Can't you
see he's through?
Stop it, that's enough already.
[Dune]
Cass... hern.
What was...
Dio.
Listen... You're the
one I've chosen.
Please understand me...
Dio... I've chosen you.
Just you... and not Casshern.
[Leda]
Okay?
[crowd murmurs]
[robot bandit L]
Look! Up there!
[Dio] To all of you who
have graced me
with your presence.
I am here to tell you
I will put an end to the ruin...
I will also defeat Casshern and
attain eternal life as a result.
Hear me...! I will become...
...the second coming
of the great Braiking Boss...
...and will create a world
where us robots
can truly thrive!
As long as you
follow my lead...
every one of you will never
have to fear death again!
[crowd cheers]
[Leda thinks] Although
this army is strong,
it won't be enough
to take down Casshern...
We must increase
its size ten-fold.
[robot bandit I] Luna? the girl
who was murdered ages ago?
[robot bandit J] I've heard
rumors that she's still alive.
[crowd continues to cheer]
[Leda thinks] There's simply no
way Luna could be alive.
[Leda thinks] I'll need to make
sure I wipe out anything
and everything that could
potentially stand in my way.
[Casshern thinks]
If Luna is alive...
...I must find a
way to see her...
All of the answers
I seek lie with her.
[Casshern thinks]
I will find her.
[Dune sobs]
♪ closing song ♪
[Casshern] There was a man
who acted as a sentinel
towards human beings...
...even after the world
had passed them by.
[Casshern] Next time...
By One's Calling.