Murder... Luna.
[Braiking Boss] But... now that
she has ended the ruin...
she's afforded a life that
eternity could never match.
Hello I'm Luna...
I shall... grant you healing..
Now... Come.
[Braiking Boss]
Is this a coincidence...
...or is this
the will of God...?
Or...
[robot refugee A]
Lady Luna!
[Braiking Boss] Has the
world really been saved?
[Luna lightly gasps]
Friender...
I know what I'm doing...
Just gonna take a peek...
It's the smell...
I recognize it from somewhere.
[Friender howls]
[Ringo laughs]
Gorgeous!
[Ringo thinks] I wish I could
show this to Ohji and Lyuze.
These will all bloom again...
...for next season.
I have to admit,
I never would have
imagined you to have
a knack for raising flowers.
Yeah well I'm just
as surprised as you are.
[Lyuze]
When I first started,
all I was doing was
giving Ringo a hand...
but I've found it
to be a lot of fun...
We're talking about
turning the entire area
into a field of flowers.
And I'm hoping to add...
...some more colors.
Really...?
How would you do that?
Ohji's researching
some fertilizers.
Oh yeah?
I see... I guess that's why
he's been locked away in
his room so much lately.
He would try to change
the color of the sky...
...as long as he knew it
would make Ringo happy.
[Lyuze groans lightly]
[metal disintegrating]
Lyuze!
[Lyuze]
I'm okay.
[Ringo]
Lyuze!
[Ringo out of breath]
Ringo.
Guess what I found!
Just on the other
side of the cliff...
There's a sea...!
The water's so
sparkly and pretty...!
I can't wait to
show you two... Hey, Ohji!!
It's been awhile...
since I've been to the sea.
[Casshern]
Let's go... Shall we?
[Ringo]
Ohji! I found the sea...!
The sea, the sea, the sea!!
I'm so... happy.
[Ringo laughs]
[Ohji]
That sweet girl...
...it's as if she's forgotten
all about the ruin.
[Ohji sighs]
[Ringo crying]
[Ohji] But... none of
that matters anymore.
[Ohji] How long have
we been here...?
I've had such a
good time of late...
it's hard for me to remember.
[Ohji] To be honest,
I feel like kicking myself
for dragging her around
the wastelands like I did,
putting her in danger.
[Ohji] I never thought doing
these little projects for her
could make me so... so...
Make me so happy...
Gorgeous.
[Lyuze] Since the four of us
have been living together,
not a day has passed
where I haven't found
something that's made
me truly happy...
This is the first time in
my life I've felt this way.
Looking back I'm really
glad I didn't kill you...
It would've been a mistake.
[Ringo laughs]
[Ringo]
Ohji, I'm gonna make
your workshop smell
just like the sea!
You're gonna love it...!
And if these aren't enough
I'll bring more 'cause
there's plenty to choose from...
Friender said he'd
help me carry them.
[Ringo] The fertilizer you're
making is gonna help all the
flowers bloom
some friends, right?
And lots of
different colors too!
I can't wait...!
They'll be so pretty!
[Ringo]
Hey Ohji...
What's your favorite color...?
Mine's definitely green...
Or, maybe Casshern's red...
But I also really like
the color of Lyuze's hair.
[Ringo]
More than anything
I love being
held by you, Ohji...
It's the best
feeling in the world.
[Luna in a panicked voice]
No...! Get back!
Lady Luna... heal me!
[metal ding]
No... Keep the ruin
away from me...!
Anything that carries death
must be destroyed...!
No exceptions!
[robot refugee]
Luna!!
[multiple metal slicing]
[Luna]
Eternal life...
Please come quickly...
I must eradicate this death.
[Braiking Boss]
You've gone too far, Luna...
I thought you were
going to stop the ruin.
[Luna] A long time ago...
I was forced to grant death.
[Luna]
Day after day...
I murdered...
At night I would
hear them cry...
...wailing and suffering.
It is wholly unnatural
for those who are
given life to die...
For death is an impure evil...
and I must destroy it.
But... ending the
ruin is... death...
You may not realize it
but you are still spreading
death like you used to.
[Luna]
Yes, temporarily...
But once it's over,
death will disappear from
this world like it should...
...and then eternal life
will begin anew.
Luna.
[Casshern] I think you
and Ringo have gone too far.
Nah... You know,
Ohji did make it
especially for Ringo...
What we have
isn't nearly enough...
We need to keep planting.
[Lyuze] Thing is, it's getting
harder for me to walk.
[Lyuze gasps as she falls]
Lyuze no!
[Casshern]
Hang in there...!
Don't you die!
I don't want to...
die either.
Casshern... Remember when
I told you that every day
I'd found something that
made me truly happy?
Today it's this...
I was able to think
"I don't want to die."
I think I've...
lived my life to the fullest...
It's been... the best.
Lyuze.
[Casshern begins to cry]
[Ringo continues to cry]
[thunder cracks]
Very soon...
the ruin will disappear...
Soon the eternal world...
[Luna]
Casshern.
Casshern is coming.
[thunder cracks]
[battle cries]
[robot bandit A]
Casshern...!
Why did you come here?!
[fighting and yelling]
[Casshern]
If you have forgotten death...
Then why have you
also forgotten what it
means to be alive?
[Casshern]
I will...
So much death...
It must end soon...
Casshern is...
the bringer of death.
I hate it.
[Braiking Boss] Do you
intend to kill Luna?
[Braiking Boss] What made
you change your mind?
At this point...
...there's no sense in
fighting you anymore...
However I bear the
responsibility for those
I have brought here.
[Braiking Boss chuckles]
Sorry but I can't let you pass.
You haven't...
received her healing?
[Braiking Boss]
Apparently not...
It's time we fought, Casshern.
[Luna]
Kill him...
Hurry, do it quickly!
If answers are all
you are looking for,
then I'm afraid this is
all I can offer you.
[Braiking Boss laughs]
[Braiking Boss builds
to a battle cry]
Casshern... both you and Luna...
This may be the price which
we must pay for interfering
with the intricacies
of life and death.
[Braiking Boss] Due to
both of your actions...
...the world has gone mad.
[Braiking Boss]
Will it return to normal?
The only one who
really knows... is God.
[Braiking Boss]
My... I certainly created
one hell of a
killing machine...
That face... I don't
know what you plan on doing...
but I can only assume it's
your own way of settling
your debt to the world.
[Braiking Boss]
Casshern...
Kill Luna once and for all.
As I lay here dying...
...I can only hope I have
atoned for my own sins.
[Braiking Boss chuckles]
Casshern.
No... ruin's coming...
and death.
Luna.
[Luna] The living bear
the stench of death.
The mere fact they are alive
means they will meet a
senseless and ugly death...
But... that shouldn't be...?
I... want to grant them
eternal life so
they may avoid it!
Luna.
Outta my way!
[thunder cracks]
That day...
...do you remember
what happened?
It was...
The blood of life and death...
[Luna and Casshern together]
Mixed together...
{Casshern]
The world...
[Luna]
[Luna and Casshern together]
Changed.
[Luna] You aren't
going to kill me?
[Casshern]
No, I won't...
There are still individuals
who seek you out,
in search of life...
It is your duty to help them.
And... it's okay if
I grant them eternal life?
[Casshern] If survival
is what they want,
then it's better
if they have it...
I cannot deny them that...
However...
If you...
...or anyone forgets
the face of death...
...then I will return.
[thunder cracks followed
by Casshern screaming]
[older Ringo] Casshern
was never seen again...
He became death for
those who will never
know what it means to die.
[older Ringo]
As for me...
I became the first to live
a life where death
wasn't an option,
but a reality that one must
face in the future.
[older Ringo] When every life in
the world becomes like mine...
I'll get to see
Casshern again!
[older Ringo]
And until then...
...I will continue, to live.