[LUNA GASPS]
[CASSHERN YELLS]
Now then...
Aren't any of you
willing to fight Sophita?
No volunteers at all?
[WARRIORBOTS YELL]
Come on... let's fight...
There's got to be one of you
is up to the challenge... yes?
[WARRIORBOT 3]
It's the Angel of Ruin!
[WARRIORBOT 4] Sophita!
[CRASHING SOUND]
[WARRIORBOT 4 YELLS]
None of you are
willing to fight Sophita?
Darn.
[WARRIORBOT 5 SCREAMS]
I don't want
to die yet!
Are you sure about that?
[WARRIORBOT 5 SCREAMS]
[CRASHING SOUND]
Aww...
[GREEN OGRE]
Your obsession with fighting
has grown troublesome, Sophita.
Or should I say Angel of Ruin?
[SOPHITA] I don't
care for that name.
It's Sophita... and
I fight because I love it.
What would be
the point in fighting?
The ruin is coming so
why hurry towards it?
Because Sophita loves
to fight, nothing more.
In a much different
time and place
you would have become
a famous warrior...
Making a name for
yourself and spreading it
throughtout the land just as
I did protecting Braiking Boss.
But with that
arm of yours
you can no longer
fight for yourself...
The ruin has
caught up to you.
[CRUMBLING]
[WARRIORBOT 6]
Hey! Watch it!
[WARRIORBOT 7]
Don't mock us!
[THUD]
[CRASHING SOUND]
[GREEN OGRE] That's enough
you couldn't handle her
even if you were brand new.
One of these days I'll replace
this dreaded arm of mine...
When I do I'll cut you down...
I look forward to that day.
[SOPHITA LAUGHS]
[CASSHERN THINKING]
Who am I...?
One who can only
bring about ruin?
What reason do
I have to go on living?
I'm the one who took the life
of the Sun that was named Moon.
[SOPHITA]
Is it really necessary to
have a reason to live and fight?
You have an exquisite body.
You look brand new.
There's not a single
scuff anywhere.
Anyways tell me...
Would you like to
fight Sophita, Mister?
But why not...?
What about just a few
minutes of sparring?
I'm sorry.
[SOPHITA] Oh come on! You
look so strong and graceful!
I wouldn't say I'm strong...
just unable to die.
Oh my.
If you're incapable of dying,
then that means you and
I can go on fighting forever.
Why do you seem
so pleased by that?
It's because...
fighting is wonderful.
Fighting is living.
Fighting is the only
thing that Sophita
can enjoy in this life...
It truly makes
her feel alive!
[WARRIORBOT 8]
An outsider!
[WARRIORBOT 9]
Perfect!
[WARRIORBOT 10]
Hand over those legs.
I do not want to fight.
You heard him...!
Now back off!
If you want him,
then you'll have to fight
through Sophita first.
[WARRIORBOT 11]
The Angel of Ruin...
Get 'em!
[SOPHITA GRUNTS]
[WARRIORBOT 11 YELLS]
Go on get out of here!
[THUD]
[WARRIORBOT 10 SCREAMS]
Wow...! You're just what
Sophita hoped you would be!
A natural born fighter who is
not afraid of using his talents!
Stay away from me.
But why...
After we've finally met?
[CASSHERN THINKING]
I don't get it...
It seems like the only thing
that happens here is violence...
Why can't I avoid it?
[CRUMBLING]
I thought I told you
to stay away from me.
[SOPHITA SIGHS]
I can't do that.
You see...
I can't leave you alone
until you
fight me first...
Please fight Sophita...
[CASSHERN]
Don't look at me like that.
The last thing I want
to do is fight someone...
And I certainly don't
want to ruin someone.
[SOPHITA]
You don't enjoy it?
How can you
not enjoy fighting?
I don't really see
how anyone could.
Well Sophita likes it...
It gets hot right here
whenever I'm fighting...
So... that's why... I love it.
Then I guess you and I will just
never understand each other.
[CASSHERN]
If someone showed me a way
to avoid fighting altogether...
I'd give up this
body in a second.
[CLANG]
Great now what...?
He doesn't want anything
to do with me...
This is why Sophita
hates using words...
Nobody ever understands
Sophita's feelings.
[GREEN OGRE]
Alright, Sophita, I give.
Let's fight, just
like you wanted.
Fine... I'd rather fight
you than no one at all,
so let's do this.
[WARRIORBOT 12 YELLS]
[SOPHITA LAUGHS]
[WARRIORBOT 14 YELLS]
[SOPHITA] I don't want to
ruin you, I really don't...
But the one I really
want to fight refuses,
so I'm left with no choice.
Please forgive me.
[WARRIORBOTS GRUNT ANGRILY]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[CRASHING SOUND]
Your skills are as
excellent as ever...
I'm impressed.
Would you rather fight
Sophita... or chat?
Am I good enough for you now?
Well... maybe... but...
I doubt Sophita...
will burn from the battle.
I guess we'll never
know unless we try, huh?
You are the
Angel of Ruin.
You cant help it that you
must ruin anyone around you.
That sound about
right... Sophita?
You become overwhelmed
with passion...
...and excitement.
You experience the joy
of living when you fight.
Heh...
That is exactly the kind
of woman that you are.
Come at me!
[GREEN OGRE GRUNTS]
[SOPHITA YELLS]
["PING" SOUND]
[SOPHITA GASPS]
[GREEN OGRE GRUNTS]
[GREEN OGRE YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[CRUMBLING]
Heh, heh...
You just made it lighter.
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
Prepare... to be ruined!
[SOPHITA GASPS]
But why ...? Your arm!
Oh it's nothing...
Unfortunately.
[SOPHITA GASPS]
[GREEN OGRE YELLS]
[CRASHING SOUND]
[GREEN OGRE GRUNTS]
I would expect
nothing less from
the one who killed
the Sun named Moon.
Tell me, why did
you attack her?
Is it because
you like violence?
[GREEN OGRE] That's a
simple enough question.
Unlike her,
I actually value my life,
so I only get involved in
conflict when I have to,
as opposed to
when I desire it.
Still... Answer me.
It was for life...
Because if I devour you,
I will be able to live
for all eternity...
I planned to lure you out
by using her as bait and
it seems I have succeeded.
So you want to live
like everyone else.
I told you...
I will be revived one day...
and I will cut you to pieces!
Sounds like you've become
jaded... about everything.
[GREEN OGRE]
What do you expect
in a world where
nothing is born...?
The only thing
left to do is survive.
[GREEN OGRE GRUNTS]
Then you should leave.
Otherwise the ground
beneath that's your feet
will become your grave.
[GREEN OGRE] The coming of
the ruin will soon be upon us,
but it would seem
that battling you
only has the potential
for shortening my life.
I must pass.
Can any form of joy be found
while living in
this kind of a world?
The repairman in this
town breaks healthy robots
on a daily basis as
a means of eeking out a life...
Making money by
doing the repairs...
Sophita lived like that
for awhile as well.
Then one day I realized...
...that If I make the
effort to break someone
I should try to enjoy it...
I mean, where's the harm
if we're both passionate,
and if we get hurt so what...?
Know what I mean?
But even so fighting isn't
meant to be enjoyable.
[SOPHITA] Sophita has become
accustomed to enjoying it.
If we must be ruined, I want
to feel good when it happens.
I want to feel excited when
I'm ruined... doing what I love.
[CASSHERN GRUNTS]
Are you in pain? What's wrong?
Your wound...
It's normal for me...
No matter how hurt I am,
it always heals soon afterward.
Oh my... you sure
are strong. Mister.
I can see how dying would be
difficult with that ability.
I'm sorry.
[CASSHERN]
Why don't we rest tonight?
I love you... Mister...
[SOPHITA GRUNTS]
[CRUMBLING]
Come on...
Let's fight!
It's the only way Sophita
knows how to share
her feelings with you.
To share...
your feelings?
This is my favorite feeling.
[CASSHERN] Don't.
Ready?
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[SPLASH]
[CASSHERN] Stop it!
[SOPHITA] I can't!
I love you too much!
[SOPHITA GRUNTS]
[SPLASH]
[SOPHITA] I'll ruin you...
...because I love you.
Just Stop it... That's enough!
I can't...
I feel sorry for you Mister.
That is why...
you must be destroyed!
[SOPHITA GRUNTS]
[SPLASH]
Haven't you had
enough yet...?
Don't make me
go all out.
It's fine...
Sophita is a strong fighter.
I've ruined countless numbers
of robots in my day...
Just like I will
ruin you, Mister.
Because that is what you
desire more than anything else.
[SOPHITA] Wouldn't it be
nice... you could be ruined.
[CASSHERN GRUNTS]
Great huh...?
It's wonderful.
Why?
[SOPHITA GASPS]
Sophita made your
wish come true
yet you're still
standing here...
How come?
I'm so happy...
that I didn't
have to harm you.
I stayed who I am this time.
I didn't hurt you in any way...
It's probably because you
never intended to kill me.
[CASSHERN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Mister...
Please don't die.
[SOPHITA]
There was no warmth.
I didn't feel the usual
fire in my chest
when I fought against you.
Sophita has only
grown close to others
who have been within
range of her deadly saber...
Until today this saber has been
the only method of
communicating her feelings.
[CASSHERN] And yet your
feelings were very clear...
...even without the blade.
The fact is you just
tried to save my life.
And you made
yourself vulnerable
by trying to
help me in a fight.
[SOPHITA]
Tell me something.
What is your name, Mister?
My name?
[SOPHITA]
In all the battles I've been in,
I've never once asked
for an opponent's name...
but I no longer
want to fight you.
So please tell me... your name.
It's Casshern.
[SOPHITA] Casshern...
That's a wonderful name...
I'm going now.
We'll never have to fight
again... for all eternity.
Please... Don't be sad
you're incapable of dying...
Just live your life
and look forward to
meeting Sophita again.
So...
Goodbye Casshern.
[CASSHERN THINKING]
That day, I learned of one life
that continued onward in
this ever-ruining world.
♪ closing song ♪
[CASSHERN]
She says to me...
"You were the one who
led the world into ruin."
Next time, The Man who
killed the Sun named Moon.