[water dripping]
[thud]
[metal shattering rock]
[stone clanking
across the surface]
[Dune grunts as he struggles]
[Dune bellows]
[heavy impact and
stones shattering]
[silence except for
a light gust of wind]
[Dune grunts]
[impact]
[Casshern struggles]
That's Luna's blood?
[rock breaks]
These... hands killed her.
[Dune grunts as he struggles]
[Dune]
I don't remember...
What was I trying
to grab that day...?
Who was it...
Who?
Hey there...
You sure you're alright?
[Lyuze]
I'm glad if you are.
[Casshern]
I haven't said a word.
Some things don't
need to be said...
...in order for them
to be understood.
Come on...
There's nothing for us here.
Let's move on.
[Lyuze gasps as she trips]
[sonic speed]
Are you alright?
I'm okay...
[Lyuze laughs]
Thanks for that.
Just took a little
tumble, that's all.
[Lyuze] It's bizarre having you
of all people worrying about me.
When I'm the one
who's supposed to
be following you.
[fragment skitters
across surface]
[Casshern] Looks like
they came through here
but couldn't go any further.
The landscape is dry
and vast it's no surprise
they weren't able to
make it out alive...
This hard pan is
a robotic graveyard.
Never thought I'd hear
empathy coming out
of your mouth, Casshern.
[Lyuze]] All these robots will
be able to rest in peace now...
Knowing someone out
there actually cared.
Is something wrong?
You see that black
mound out there?
[sound of shattering rocks]
Is he dead?
[shattering]
No... Not yet.
Well... it doesn't look
like he has much longer.
[Dune grunts]
[Dune]
I cannot die...
Not until this hand...
grabs something.
He wants to live.
Yes... He's trying his best.
[Dune grunts]
[Dune bellows]
Wait... Don't move!
[Dune groans as he struggles]
[Lyuze]
He's lucky...
To have someone by
his side in the
middle of this wasteland.
[Lyuze]
Still...
I wonder...
What exactly is it
he's trying to grasp...?
Just who is it that's...
...inspiring him to live?
Life... has an inherent desire
to survive... at all costs.
He has a soul.
And that soul...
will not allow him
to die so easily.
Lyuze... You should get
some rest while you can.
I think I'll be alright.
The more I get to know you...
...the harder you
are to understand.
I used to think...
you had no soul...
that your only purpose in life
was to fight and destroy.
You know... I hardly
understand it myself...
It's just...
Perhaps people tend
to develop their weaknesses...
...when they protect someone
other than themselves.
Someone to... protect.
[Ringo laughs]
Doesn't it feel great... Ohji?!
Sure does.
I feel like I can do
anything I want today!
Oh yeah...?
So what do you want to do?
[Ringo ponders]
Hmm...
What about you?
Well I don't know...
[Ohji]
Hmm...
[Ringo playfully]
[Ringo and Ohji
playfully "hmm" back and forth]
Ringo, hold on?
It's okay Ohji, I'm fine!
But... Doesn't it hurt
whenever you do that?
No, not really...
I love the feeling
of this wind!
Ringo.
I feel... a whole lot better
when I'm not wearing it...
...even though it is
harder to breathe.
[Ringo laughs]
[Ohji thinks] I want
to do everything
I possibly can to
provide for you.
[Ohji thinks] That is
my one and only wish.
[Ringo laughs]
Doesn't it feel good Ohji?
Did he die?
[Dune]
I must go on.
I want to live.
[Dune] I want to hold
something in my hands...
...and feel its warmth.
[Lyuze]
Hold something...?
What exactly?
I wish I knew.
[thud]
[Dune groans]
I don't understand.
Why even try to move on...?
How do you work
up the desire...
...when you don't even
know where the path leads?
[Dune yells]
Dune?
You know this guy?
He was a guard...
...who protected Luna...
with my sister.
Him... really?
[Lyuze]
Yeah.
He was so feared
it was said that if you
even looked at him...
...you would die an
instantaneous death,
just from the
sight of him alone.
The God of Death...
...Dune.
So the God of Death
actually... protected Luna.
[Lyuze]
He loved Luna...
...more than anyone
else that ever lived.
He guarded her fearlessly...
The God of Death... Dune.
[Casshern]
So there was someone.
Just one person...
One being who was still
standing after I
annihilated the world...
after I destroyed Luna.
[Lyuze] I have a feeling he's
still trying to protect
Luna even now.
[stone shattering]
[Friender growls]
[projectile hissing]
[impact explosion]
[Lyuze gasps]
[heavy metallic foot falls]
[Robot bandit yells out]
[fighting sounds
and sword slicing metal]
[Robot bandit B] I know you...
you're Casshern!
[Robot bandit C]
Really?
[Robot bandit D]
That's Casshern?
[Casshern] I'm warning
you to walk away.
[Robot bandit C]
Devour him!
[Robot bandit C bellows]
[Robot bandit D]
Die!
[Robot bandit D groans]
[thud]
[Robot bandit B]
Kill him!
[Dune]
Casshern.
Lady Luna!
I am the one...
called Casshern.
Casshern.
[Robot bandit B yells
out after being hit]
[thud]
Luna!
[explosion]
[Dune gulps]
My Dune.
[Luna]
You are no God of Death...
You are my Guardian Angel.
Dune... Live on...
Dune.
[Dune]
You're my enemy!
[Lyuze cries out]
[Dune bellows]
[slicing dings]
[Casshern grunts in pain]
[thud]
Casshern...
You are my enemy...!
My nemesis...! Luna's killer!
[slicing dings]
[Dune]
My scourge!
[impact]
[slicing dings, fighting
and explosions]
There's no point in fighting!
Both of you stop it!
Lady Luna!
But why...? You were lucky
enough to survive the ruin...
What reason could you
possibly have to fight anymore?
Why...? Dune...
[Dune groans loudly in pain]
[thud]
[Dune]
Lady Luna.
More people are praying...
...they will come to me
today in hopes of survival.
So too... will those who
have accepted their ruin.
[Dune groans]
I won't forgive you.
That's enough, Dune...
Stop...! Please...
You don't have...
to protect her anymore...
Because.
The Luna you
devoted your life to...
...isn't actually dead...
She is alive.
Lady Luna... is alive?
[Lyuze]
Yes, very much so...
She's living somewhere
beyond these plains.
[Luna]
Don't cry, Dune...
It's imperative I live...
...for the sake of everyone
who has perished.
[Dune]
Lady Luna.
What I tried to grasp...
...that day so long ago...
...wasn't you, Casshern.
[Dune] What my now
withered hand sought was...
...Lady Luna.
[Ringo]
Guess what, Ohji...
[Ohji]
What's that?
[Ringo] I know what
I want to do now!
I want to make your most
desired wish come true!
[Ohji]
Is that right...?
That makes me very happy.
[Lyuze] You said that people
tend to develop weakness
whenever they must protect
someone other than themselves...
[Lyuze]
I think you're wrong.
When you have
someone to protect...
...you become compassionate.
[Casshern] What
people seek when the
depths of despair and
death are upon them...
...may be the silhouettes
of the ones they love.
[Casshern] In order
for one to exist...
there is always someone
nearby in need
of their protection.
Next time...
For the Strength to Believe.