[Lyuze coughs]
[Casshern]
Are you alright...?
Maybe we should rest.
[Lyuze]
No, I'll be fine.
[water rushing]
Woah...
What is that thing?
[Ringo]
Ohji...!
There's a creepy little
thing crawling on my nose!
[Ohji]
A creepy little thing...?
Oh right... you've never
seen a bug before have you?
[Ringo]
A bug...?
That's what you call it?
[buzz]
It flew away...!
Bye bye...! Mister Bug!
What is with this place?
What are flowers doing here?
[Ringo surprises]
Rar...!
[Ringo laughs and then giggles]
Did I scare you?
You maybe startled me a bit...
[Lyuze laughs]
[Lyuze]
Ringo, I have to ask...
What's going on with your face?
[Lyuze]
You look like a clown!
[Ringo giggles]
[Lyuze] Hey Casshern...
look who I found...
Check out Ringo's new look.
Ringo.
[Ringo continues to giggle]
[Robot bandit A]
Lord Dio!
[Robot bandit B]
Long live Dio!
[Robot bandit C] The world is
yours for the taking!
[Robot bandit D] We'll follow
your every command Lord Dio!
[Leda] Why won't you
even acknowledge them...
Because they're nothing
more than a mob
with self interests...
They only pledge loyalty
to me because they
want to be saved.
[Dio]
But I want more.
[Dio] I want every living
being to worship me,
to bow before me in awe.
Don't you see?
You already have that.
You're wrong...!
Casshern does!
[Dio]
I must first defeat him...
that must happen.
Until then...
I cannot become all powerful.
Why are you letting
that get to you... Dio?
[Leda]
Just take a deep breath...
You're blowing this all
out of proportion.
[Leda]
All is not lost.
[Robot bandit E] Lord Dio,
we have a problem!
[metal crashing]
[Robot bandit E] This robot was
one of a group who left the
castle two days ago
in search of Luna.
So then what
happened to the others?
[Robot bandit E]
They're gone...
Apparently two unknown
robots defeated them all.
[Dio]
Who did this to you?
[Robot bandit F]
I'm sorry Lord Dio...
I didn't catch their names...
but they said
they knew where...
...to find Luna.
[metal smashing]
Dio... Seize this opportunity...
Destroy them and show
the world your strength.
I see no benefit in
fighting unless
it's against Casshern.
[Leda thinks] Defeating
Casshern won't be easy...
Perhaps a quicker option
would be just to capture Luna.
[Ringo giggles]
[Ringo] Ooh, Lyuze...!
I want to give you
something really special!
[Ringo] Here... Ohji took this
piece of broken glass and
polished it up for me.
[Ringo]
Isn't it pretty?
But I don't want to take
something that's
important to you.
[Ringo]
I don't mind...
Besides, I like the
flowers much better!
[Ringo giggles]
[Ringo] When Ohji
gave it to me...
he said that when
you look through the glass,
you can see a whole
new and different world.
A world where there's no ruin...
sparkling in emeralds!
[Lyuze]
A different world, huh?
Thanks Ringo...
I love it.
[Ringo playfully
giggles and laughs]
Ohji... I saw Ringo's arm
bleeding the other day...
What's going on?
[Casshern] Is she a
human or something?
Do us a favor
and forget about it.
Look Ohji...
I want to protect
Ringo and Lyuze...
[Casshern]
Finding Luna...
...and saving those two from
ruin are all I care about.
[Ohji]
And why is that?
[Casshern] I can't
explain it very well but...
...recently for some reason...
...those two have
become very special to me.
I see.
Special to you... huh?
[thud and rolling on the ground]
[Ohji]
I was an ideal employee,
following Braiking Boss'
orders to a T...
But that loyalty indirectly
lead me to cause the ruin.
[Ohji] In the aftermath,
I quickly spiraled into despair
and abandoned Braiking Boss...
...to wander the world
aimless and without purpose.
[Ohji grimacing]
[metal breaking and
Ohji screams]
[Ohji]
Is there any hope for
salvation in a world as
forsaken as this?
[Ohji]
Everywhere I turned...
I saw meaningless fighting...
Robots killing each
other for no reason.
[Ohji] The walking dead
waiting for the end.
[Ohji] Foolish robots massacring
weaker humans as if it
were some kind of sport,
life had become a silly game
to them and nothing more.
[Ohji] It was
truly a living hell.
[Ohji] I no longer
held the will to live,
let alone hope for
something better.
[Ohji cries out as he trips]
[Ohji] I fell into
a deep depression...
...and the only way I
saw out of it was death.
[Female voice] You
must go on living...
Don't give in.
[Baby Ringo cries]
[door being kicked]
[Baby Ringo continues to cry]
[Ohji] I could hear through
that baby's cries someone
telling me to live...
and to not give in.
[Ohji yells]
[Metal crashing into
metal as Ohji cries out]
[Baby Ringo cries]
[Ohji]
I found her wrapped in
clothes a human
would wear,
inside the shell of
a fallen robot.
[Ohji] Her earnest cries
defied the ruin to its core.
[Ohji]
A baby, alive and healthy,
in a world crumbling around her.
[Ohji]
It was a miracle...
...for her to have survived
such a living hell.
That is why...
...Ringo is a very
special person to me.
Amazing...
Two robots did this alone?
[Vulcan] I had a feeling
you'd come here.
It's been quite awhile...
Lord Dio...and Leda.
[Leda]
Let's go.
[Leda] We're better off not
getting involved with them.
[Vulcan] There's no need
to be rude... Lady Leda.
[Robot bandit E]
How disrespectful...
Who are those two?
[Leda] Before we even existed
there were two robots
who were considered
the strongest in the Empire.
[Leda]
Vulcan and Mars...
You're looking at 'em.
[Robot bandit E] Talk about
relics from the past.
From the looks of it
you two seem to have
been lying about
knowing were Luna is.
Just walk away.
[Vulcan]
We were...
It was all an attempt to
lure you from your castle.
[Mars] If it wasn't for you
and all your meddling Dio,
we could have peacefully
succumbed to ruin by now.
Having been known as the
strongest warriors
within the entire empire.
[Dio] And that's your
reasoning behind killing me?
[Vulcan] That and we
figured while we're at it...
we might as well
take over the robotic army
you've been working
so hard to form.
[Dio] Fighting you two would
not only be a waste of my time,
it would be pointless.
[explosion]
[Dio cries out]
[Mars cries out]
That's enough.
[Leda] I will swear my
allegiance to you both...
As long as you promise
to spare his life!
[Mars chuckles]
Oh how can I refuse
when it's the lovely
Lady Leda begging me to?
[Mars]
It's a deal...
I take it you can guide
us to the castle then?
[Dio grimaces]
[water flowing]
[Dio] Is that
you Braiking Boss?
[Braiking Boss] You
need to control yourself...
Here we are in a day
and age when robots
are being ruined by the
thousands and yet you still
insist on fighting
your own kind.
[Braiking Boss]
In the shape you're in now,
there isn't a chance in hell
you could defeat those two.
But why...?
I don't understand...
...please tell me!
We are perfectly identical...
...in both skills and specs...
So explain to me why
I'm inferior to Casshern!
[Braiking Boss] It's simple.
Casshern is a killing machine...
He was the strongest
in the robotic army...
and was devoid of any
traces of emotion that
could hold him back.
[Braiking Boss] But the
Casshern of old is no more...
Now he possesses emotion,
much like a human being
who wears his
heart on his sleeve.
[Braiking Boss] He is finally
searching for his purpose in
life and is beginning
to understand
what it is he must do.
[Braiking Boss]
He's protecting someone,
but it's been a struggle...
and he's learning what it feels
like to be utterly helpless,
and the terror
that goes with it...
Just like a human.
It's the same with
those two dimwits.
[Braiking Boss] Their goal
was not to defeat you,
but to make you afraid.
[Braiking Boss] To make
you fear being ruined.
[Braiking Boss]
To make you feel helpless.
On that day,
the fate of both you
and Casshern was decided.
[Dio]
What day was that?
[Braiking Boss]
The day he killed Luna...
Whether he wants it or not,
he must carry the
weight of destiny
on his shoulders.
Casshern is the sole person
responsible for turning
this world into a
wasteland of ruin...
He doesn't have this
obsessive fixation on
defeating a single person
like you do Dio.
If I may be so blunt,
you can't even
take care of yourself...
...let alone anyone else.
You will never have
what it takes to
defeat Casshern.
Don't ever utter that
name in my presence again!
[water rippling]
[explosion]
[Leda]
Dio!
I knew you would save me!
[Vulcan]
In the Valley of Ruin,
there's a stone that will
lead you to Luna.
[Vulcan]
Just north of the lake...
Now please, save me.
Aren't you gonna
finish him off?
What's the point...?
There's no way he could
ever defeat me
without Mars helping him.
[Dio] Let the ruin
take care of him.
[Vulcan]
Braiking Boss!?
Well it looks like Mars
was defeated rather easily.
[Vulcan]
Damn you...
Why did you create
Dio and the others...?
Why did you abandon us?
[Vulcan]
Why Braiking Boss, why?
That's good...
Show me how mad you are.
[Vulcan cries out]
[metal breaking and
Vulcan cries out]
Those last few years
must have been tough...
Now you can rest easy.
Ohji...! Come here!
It says it's a stone
that has the power
to heal people.
It's Luna...!
It must mean that
she's been here before!
I can feel a breeze
coming from inside.
Is that right?
[Ohji]
There's stairs.
[Ringo laughs]
I wish these peaceful
days could go on... forever.
[Casshern] A past which
cannot be erased...
is resurrected along
with a horde of
appalling memories.
[Casshern] Next time...
The Glass Cradle.