Now die... Luna.
[ROBOT GUARD A]
This way. Quickly.
[METAL BREAKING]
[ROBOT BANDIT A LAUGHS]
[ROBOT GUARD A]
Stay behind me!
[GUST OF WIND]
[ROBOT GUARD A]
Why are you chasing us?
[ROBOT BANDIT A] Why...? It's
a simple matter of survival.
[ROBOT BANDIT A]
Once we're done you
will live on as a part of us,
so you better be appreciative...
[ROBOT BANDIT B] Plus...
There's no place for
hope amongst all this ruin.
[ROBOT GUARD B] Protecting
hope is our sworn duty...
[ROBOT GUARD B]
Proceed if you dare.
[ROBOT BANDIT C LAUGHS]
[ROBOT BANDIT A]
Now die!
[ROBOT BANDIT B] Looks like
you're the only one left.
[ROBOT BANDIT B] It's time for
hope to take its last breath.
[SHATTERING]
[JANIS HOLDS A NOTE]
[ROBOT BANDIT B CONFUSED]
[JANIS CONTINUES TO HOLD A NOTE]
[ROBOT BANDIT B] What the?
♪ I wanna be... a star. ♪
♪ I wanna be a star... ♪
♪ ...that never stops. ♪
[ROBOT BANDIT A
GRUNTS IN CONFUSION]
♪ All shining
down on you. ♪
♪ I wanna be a moon... ♪
♪ ...like a gentle wind. ♪
♪ I'll softly touch
your face... ♪
♪ Feel my breath... ♪
♪ ...when you close
your eyes at night. ♪
♪ It's alright, you were not ♪
♪ the only one... ♪
♪ I will be the whisper
in your voice. ♪
♪ I'll find your day... ♪
[ROBOT BANDIT D] Shut up!
[JANIS] ♪ Do you wanna be... ♪
[ROBOT BANDIT] Quiet!
♪ If there is a
choice... dream. ♪
[SHATTERING]
[CAR ENGINE WHIRRING]
[RINGO]
Is this...
I'm sure...
Casshern had a
hand in this.
But I have no idea
what the circumstances
might have been.
Casshern.
[RINGO GIGGLES]
[OHJI]
Hmm.
Wasn't that song so pretty?
So why?
Tell me... What is it
that makes you sing?
[JANIS]
You tell me...
What makes you kill?
[CASSHERN] I don't
have much choice.
[JANIS]
Do you kill...
...in order to gain life?
You see... I was
born to be a singer...
That's why I do it...
So were you born with
the desire to kill
your own species?
I believe my teasing
has gone on long enough.
Thank you very much...
...for saving me.
[JANIS]
You are a wonder.
You have such immense power...
For some reason you
carry it around on your
shoulders as if it were guilt.
[CASSHERN] But is
there even a reason...
...for one to have
this much power?
In this world...
...nothing is without reason...
Nothing.
[JANIS] It is up to the
individual to find reason...
If one can find it,
one is capable
of moving on without confusion.
It's that simple really...
My life would be empty
without singing...
I'm fairly certain...
...you will find a good
cause to fight one day.
[JANIS]
Hmm.
[WIND GUST PICKS UP]
Recently...
I've been on a bit
of a journey...
...towards a special place.
Special place?
I've been trying to reach
it for a long time...
It has become the
journey of my life.
So wait...
Are you sure it still exists?
I don't really know...
So many places have
changed since the
ruin spread everywhere...
And it's happening
so much faster than...
...I could have ever imagined.
However... I still believe.
That everyone...
...must have
hope in their lives.
You are... a great wonder.
No I think we both are.
Tell me... what are you
going to do now?
Well maybe I'll...
...go with you?
[LYUZE] Janis,
the woman with a
voice that can drive one
to forget the horrors of ruin.
The Song Princess.
The man who
spreads destruction...
...is with the woman...
...who brings relief to
the world's stricken...
Like a shield and a spear.
Their deaths were
not your fault...
...so why are you so
troubled by the sight of them?
The ruin is what caused this.
And you believe
that to be the truth?
[SNAPPING]
[CASSHERN]
Well... I...
[JANIS] What is it
you're frightened of?
Me...? You think I'm frightened?
Am I incorrect?
[CASSHERN]
I don't know.
I have no idea.
[CASSHERN]
The reason they died...
The reason the
ruin even started...
...it's all my fault...
It's going to be fine...
It's okay...
It's not your fault.
[SPLASHING]
[ROBOT BANDIT F]
Die!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
Are you alright there?
[CASSHERN GRIMACES]
Oh my.
So then... this means...
...that you're Casshern?
[CASSHERN CONTINUES TO GRIMACE]
[ROBOT BANDIT G] I see...
No wonder you're so powerful.
[ROBOT BANDIT G]
You must be... Janis.
[CASSHERN]
How do you know us?
[ROBOT BANDIT G] Word has
been floating around recently...
...that the two of you...
...are heading for
the town of Vaasa.
[JANIS SHOCKED]
[ROBOT BANDIT G]
It seems like a lot of our
prey are heading
that direction...
...seeking any last
bits of hope...
...but they will surely
become our victims in the end.
[ROBOT BANDIT G]
You better watch your back...
Everyone's gunning
for you first.
[ROBOT BANDIT G] All
because of that detestable song.
[CASSHERN]
Hey!
[SPLASH]
[ELECTRIC POWER DOWN]
[JANIS WHIMPERS]
[WATER SPLASHING AS JANIS MOVES]
Casshern... Take me...
...there... I beg you.
[JANIS] There are
people in need,
waiting for me...
Please, help me.
[OHJI WHISTLING]
That's the song we heard before.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
[RINGO]
I wonder what Casshern
is doing right now.
[OHJI] I'd bet he's
struggling along,
doing his own thing.
[RINGO]
Huh?
But his struggle is different
than ours because
he's a fighter.
So what do ya say...?
Shall we get going?
[RINGO HUMS APPROVAL]
Vaasa.
[JANIS] Do you have any idea
how long I've been
trying to get here?
[JANIS] This is the
Vaasa Music Hall.
[LIGHTS TURN ON]
[JANIS] I heard someone
sing here a long time ago.
[JANIS] My heart was shaken
by the performance.
The song was... fleeting...
...immensely powerful.
I listened... and
I became possessed
by the song...
At that moment...
...I realized that...
...my life's dream
is to sing here.
[JANIS] I had always sang...
But from that day forward...
...I prayed that my songs would
actually touch people's hearts.
Touch their souls.
[JANIS] It's ironic when
you think about it...
As the ruin spreads
over the land,
effecting more
and more people...
...my songs seem to
touch the afflicted
more and more.
[JANIS] But the
ruin isn't stopping...
[JANIS WHIMPERS]
[JANIS] I sing...
so... that people...
...hear my songs...
and...
...feel hope... But...
Today... I will dedicate my
song towards your heart...
...and yours alone.
[LIGHTS TURNING ON]
[ROBOT VILLAGER A] Thank
goodness you made it
here safely.
I'm so glad I waited!
[LIGHTS COMING ON]
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
[RINGO]
Ohji! Hurry up!
[OHJI]
Hmm?
[RINGO]
Ohji, come on!
[LIGHTS CLICK ON]
[IMPACT]
[ROBOT BANDIT H
ROARS AS HE ATTACKS]
♪ You listen to my voice, ♪
♪ listen to my heart, ♪
♪ Now I say it clearly... ♪
♪ You listen to your voice, ♪
♪ listen to your heart, ♪
♪ Do you even smile? ♪
♪ There is nothing you can do, ♪
♪ only you can do ♪
♪ to make yourself happy... ♪
♪ You listen to your voice, ♪
♪ listen to your heart, ♪
♪ make yourself live. ♪
♪ We are free... ♪
♪ ...like water flows... ♪
♪ We are one... ♪
[SONIC SPEED]
♪ As we feel the love. ♪
♪ How long will it take... ♪
♪ ...to find a way out? ♪
♪ But she never
lost her faith... ♪
♪ and made her
way back home... ♪
♪ So we hold
each other's hands... ♪
♪ ...as we walk
along the way... ♪
♪ No more fears
and tears to fall... ♪
♪ We'll find our
way back home. ♪
[ROBOT METAL CLINKING
AND GETTING LOUDER]
[COLLISONS AND FIGHTING]
♪ We are free... ♪
♪ ...like water flows... ♪
♪ We are one... ♪
♪ as we feel the love... ♪
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
♪ How long will it take... ♪
♪ to find the way out...? ♪
♪ But she never
lost her way... ♪
♪ ...and made her
way back home... ♪
[CONTINUED FIGHTING SOUNDS]
♪ So we hold
each other's hand... ♪
♪ ...as we walk
along the way... ♪
♪ No more fears ♪
♪ and tears to fall... ♪
♪ We'll find our
way back home. ♪
♪ How long will it take... ♪
♪ ...to find a way out...? ♪
♪ But she never
lost her way... ♪
♪ ...and made
herself back home. ♪
♪ Hold each other's hand... ♪
♪ ...as we walk along the way ♪
♪ No more fears
and tears to fall... ♪
♪ We'll find our
way back home. ♪
[EXPLOSION AND SHATTERING]
♪ You listen to my voice, ♪
♪ listen to my heart, ♪
♪ Now I say it clearly... ♪
♪ You listen to your voice, ♪
♪ listen to your heart, ♪
♪ Do you even smile? ♪
♪ CLOSING SONG ♪
[CASSHERN] There was
once a forgotten girl...
...desperately holding
onto a single wish.
[CASSHERN]
Next time...
The Flower that Blooms
in the Valley of Ruin.