No way.
When I went to go visit her last week, she was fine.
I mean, we talked about shopping.
It happened just as we were heading in to see her.
Out of nowhere.
They got to her in time,
but she's in the ICU right now.
She'll be okay, though, right?
They don't think that she's gonna...
I don't know.
After seeing all that, I don't know what to think.
Oh, man.
You said we were heading.
Was Kousei with you?
Please.
Please go and save Kousei.
If he breaks again,
we're gonna lose him.
Damn it, Kousei! I know that you're home!
I'm coming up!
Listen to me!
I know you're hurting, but you
need to get your head on straight.
That competition is right around the corner!
You are gonna practice if I have to drag you!
I can't.
I can't do this.
Why does it have to end this way?
All I wanted was to play the piano
and make my mom better again.
That's all.
I didn't know
I was going to fall in love.
I can't save her.
I'm done.
There's nothing left.
Ah, look at this cute stationary!
Hey.
So, yeah, they let me come back here yesterday.
The ICU was a drag.
I'd never been in one before but I don't recommend it.
Everybody's so serious.
I'm sorry you had to see that, by the way.
We should have stuck to phone calls, Friend A.
Just saying.
Snap out of it!
Hey, what the heck?
Don't make a big deal about
coming if you're gonna be all gloomy!
What are you trying to do? Make me even sicker?
Canaeles! You and me on the roof!
But it's cold out.
I'll steal your coat.
Do it, do it, do it, do it!
One fat joke and you're going down the stairs.
Just don't eat more of the caneles.
She's light. Very light.
I always used to tell myself she was going to be fine.
She'd weathered the worst of it.
She was strong but now I... I don't know.
She loves stuffed animals and has a sweet tooth.
She's fragile. I see that now.
God, I'm a moron.
Ah!
It's snowing!
Are you playing the piano?
No, I'm not.
Of course you're not.
You're too busy moping, huh?
I just can't do it.
The people I love, they keep on leaving me.
Music just brings to mind what I've lost.
And now I'm gonna be alone.
But you have me.
You know that, right?
There's a chance they can fix me.
The surgery's set for the 18th.
Nobody knows if it'll work,
but they said there's a chance, so I'm taking it.
Just so you know,
it's your fault I'm going through with this.
Your fault that I'm struggling to live.
Why I don't have the good sense to give up.
Why I dream.
The moments we share,
I' hanging onto them
for as long as I can.
You should fight, too. Don't you think?
That's what being a musician is all about.
In a way, it's life or death
every time we step out on stage.
But I haven't touched the piano in over a week.
I'm rusty.
You were rusty when we played, too.
At least I was playing a bit
for my part time job back then.
Whatever I do now is trash.
It would take a miracle. What's the point?
You're looking down again.
There, you see?
Getting a miracle can be a cinch.
Whoa!
In the same way that you have me,
I have you, too.
You like to drink milk
'cause it washes down all those sweets.
What else do you like, though?
Do you collect stuff?
Bugs or stamps or anything?
Do you like anime?
So much that I don't know about you.
I envy Tsubaki for having all of the answers.
I want to ask you so many things.
I'm scared.
I don't wanna die.
Kousei!
Don't go! Don't leave me all alone!
I'm a moron.
She's tempestuous and capricious.
I can't read her,
but this girl is beautiful.
A vision of spring.
Friend in snow.
We're going to start the anesthesia.
Just breathe deeply.
There's this quote from the "Peanuts."
"We all need someone to kiss us good‐bye."
Her vitals are holding steady.
Patient is anesthetized.
Very good. Let's begin.
Bravo!
You're incredible!
Emi, that performance was sublime!
How does someone play like that?
Takeshi's piece blew the others out of the water,
but Emi's song was every bit as good.
I see.
She's further along,
but we're both on the same path.
Splendid work.
I didn't think Ochiai's girl would rise to the challenge.
Technically the two are neck and neck.
Spare me the gloating, you witch.
These finals are riveting.
Two prodigies in the same district?
I wonder which one's gonna win?
You were dazzled by those amateurs?
The greatest pianist of them
all has yet to grace the stage.
Hold on. Isn't that...
Yeah.
I'll give the old gal this.
Ochiai's great at lighting a
fire under the ass of her kids.
Please, Ms. Seto,
how is Arima doing back there?
He's a damn mess.
I was able to drag him down here.
Who knows if he can play?
It's two years ago all over again.
He might be done with the piano,
not just today but for the rest of his life.
Help me! Please!
Help me, anybody!
Please just let him get through it.
Very good.
Marvelous.
See that, you two?
Hey, what's wrong?
You look terrible.
I can get you something for your stomach,
if that's what's bothering you, Arima.
He might just be getting focused.
Huh? I guess,
but he looks so bad.
I gotta play.
I gotta play. I gotta play.
Arima's turn is coming.
At last!
That boy is amazing.
I'm waiting for this.
I hear that he's better than ever.
Number 23, Kousei Arima.
You're the next one up,
so please take your place in the wings.
Hold on, man! Are you good to go on?
Uh‐huh. I'll be fine.
Don't worry about me.
What?
Your face is white as a sheet.
You can't compete in this condition.
We need to get you to a doctor.
Sorry, but I've gotta play
because I'm a pianist.
I made a promise.
It's Arima!
Here he comes.
He's so cool.
I hope he doesn't faint on the way to the piano.
I'm making you remember things better left forgotten.
I'm a violinist who can't hold her bow anymore.
I'm useless!
I'll never forget about us,
no matter what happens.
I've gotta play.
All you have to do is forget about me.
Just press the reset button in your mind.
I've gotta play.
You'd be happier if we had never met, huh?
I've got to because I'm a pianist.
Arima!
Come on, kid!
Is he cracking?
It's the pressure.
But it's Arima.
You're looking down again.
Tsubaki, you dummy.
We are so not with her.
Tsubaki, I see you.
All of you.
You're all here with me.
This isn't just pesante.
It's so deep. So unhurried.
Such a rich tone for one so young.
One of Chopin's loneliest pieces.
Ballade No. 1 in G Minor, Opus 23.
Like a whispered word,
or loving touch,
it manifests so gently,
yet it's fraught with true sorrow.
Thinking about some chick you like, yeah?
You bet I am.
For now it's enough that you play what you feel.
But my heart is a sinking ship.
What a cliché.
That doesn't mean it's not true, though.
Are you gonna play that song all night,
or are you gonna comfort me already?
Guess it can't be helped.
I'm not good with words.
Everyone, the reason I'm here right now
is because I had you.
The people who play a part in my life,
the people who make my life fuller,
I can't let them down.
Maybe it's because all three of us are pianists.
We gotta say it with music.
Yeah, you're right.
That's how it is.
Whether you're sad or hurt or empty,
you have to keep playing,
'cause you're a musician.
Sure feels like I'm winging it.
We're totally winging it,
but we'll be great because we're just that awesome!
And so I play.
Not because it haunts me, but because I want to.
Heart and soul, I'm a pianist.
A musician.
You taught me that.
Amazing.
Arima's playing is incredible.
The music pouring out of him, out of his life itself,
it's sparkling with colors I can't even name!
He summons this song with all the contents of his heart.
Bearing his soul before the frost.