TAKESHI: Heroes are powerful.
They fight the good fight alone.
And when they're done,
they melt back into the night.
Kind of like he did.
[scattered applause]
Exactly like he did.
- [panting]
- That was good, right?
- He was disqualified
the moment he stopped, though.
- There's scattered applause.
They're confused.
Not that it matters.
I played for the sake
of one person.
Did it reach her?
I hope that it did.
["Hikaru Nara" playing]
♪♪
[singing in Japanese]
[scattered applause]
[Emi grunts]
- Hmm?
- Listen up, you.
- [gasps]
- This competition is a place
to show your very best.
It is not a place
for working out your issues
in public.
- Still the same
prickly old geezer. Am I right?
The stick up his butt
gets worse every year.
God help us.
Hey, Mr. Quitter.
- Ms. Seto?
- I'm practically family,
you butt-head.
- I totally meant
to say, "Hiroko"!
I guess you got a haircut.
Took me a second
to recognize you.
- Women change their hair
all the time,
not like guys,
with their one look.
After all, it's been two years.
[chuckles]
- That chick's
a stone-cold fox.
- It feels like I've
seen her somewhere before.
- Real nice, Kousei,
keeping that chick a secret.
I thought we were bros,
you monster.
- Oh, she's the one
who always visited
Kousei's mom back in the day.
- That's Hiroko Seto.
She's Japan's leading pianist.
- Hey, Koharu.
It's been a long time.
TSUBAKI: It makes sense
she would be there.
Kousei's mom and she
were classmates in college.
- I guess the friendship lasted.
- [laughs]
- Weird, huh? There's stuff
about Kousei's life
I know nothing about.
- Huh?!
- Whoa!
- [squeals]
- I, uh--
Everybody's staring
at us, Hiroko.
SAKI: Hey, Hiroko,
do you want to hold him?
- Uh, I'll give it a try.
- Make sure
you support his head.
Gently now.
- [chuckles]
- Isn't he adorable?
We decided to name him Kousei.
- Future pianist?
- Not if I have anything
to say about it.
That's a tough life for a kid.
- Now you gotta
turn him into a pianist.
- I don't know.
- Oh, look at him!
The kid's a natural.
KOUSEI: Help me.
[crying] Help me.
HIROKO: I'm sorry, Kousei.
- Mom.
- Please forgive me.
Who told you you could grow up,
you butt-head?
- You smell like an ashtray.
- Hey, now.
At least I don't smell
like a teenage boy.
[laughs] Your friends over there
look like they're
gonna burst a gasket.
- Uh...
- [yelps]
- [all gasp] We're busted!
- You're staying
for the results, right?
- Huh? Nah.
I don't care about my score,
and I'm out of the running,
anyway.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah! When you bomb
at a competition,
you don't half-ass it!
- Way to be supportive!
- Either way,
you should be there
when the results go up.
It's competition etiquette.
- [yelps]
- So which one of 'em is it,
huh? Long-haired chick?
Short-haired chick? 'Fess up.
I know you're in love
with one of 'em.
- Where do you get this stuff?
- Say what you want.
I ain't buyin' it.
Your playing told me as much.
It sang out the words,
"I love you."
Didn't you know?
Or maybe you're
pretending not to.
Emotions can be funny things.
They sneak up on you.
When you're young,
the piano turns your heart
into an open book.
Brace yourself.
Don't be a stranger, yeah?
- It's not like that.
What I'm feeling is gratitude.
After all, she's...
she's the girl
who likes my best friend,
and me...
I'm just Friend A.
- [crowd murmuring]
- All right.
We're about to post the results
of the first round.
- Look! There's my name!
- Cool.
- Is Arima on the list?
- Hard to imagine
Arima not making the cut.
- [sighs]
Heroes don't crumble.
They suck it up and fight on.
- [gasps]
- It's no surprise.
I did stop halfway.
- No way!
- [gasps]
- I did it!
There's my name, see?
- [sighs]
Guess I fell short again.
- I'll practice even harder
for next year.
- No more chances.
- I hate this.
- All that work...
what a waste.
- Takeshi.
- You played like a joke today.
What the hell have you
been doing all this time?!
All I want to do
is defeat Arima.
You couldn't even get through
that song without stopping.
Why did you even bother
with that train wreck?
What happened to the Arima
from my childhood,
my invincible rival?
Where did he go?
My hero always carries the day.
My hero's bulletproof.
You knew the moment you stopped
that they'd never bump you up
past prelims, so why?
Why do you have
that look on your face?
Heroes always win,
no matter what.
Watching you fail, it's like--
you're just another person.
- Train wreck?
Yeah, I assumed as much.
But I'm not really
in a position to make that call.
- [gasps]
- There's a rumor
Arima can't even
hear the notes.
- I guess it's true.
- I wasn't trying
to waste anybody's time.
I practiced 'til I passed out.
I gave it my all.
- You're you, no matter what.
- So if I turned in
a bad performance
despite that, I guess...
I guess that's who I am.
Right now,
that's all I'm good for.
- [gasps]
- Mozart did say
we should go on a journey.
Where this journey
is going to take me,
who can tell?
But I've taken the first step.
I'm not alone, though.
All of us are in this together.
That's right.
I'm a musician,
just like you two.
That's why I'm moving on.
[footsteps echoing]
- [sighs] He's him,
but different.
- I guess he finally found it,
a reason to play.
- During his song,
just for a moment,
it reminded me
of the boy he used to be.
[dog barking]
WATARI: Say something
to him, Tsubaki.
He's all depressed and junk
because he blew it today,
so step up.
- Maybe it's a guy thing.
You talk to him.
- [both gasp]
- I'm fine, you guys, really.
It doesn't bother me.
- Well, then, we're good.
[crossing bell ringing]
- This competition is a place
to show your very best,
not working out
your issues in public.
[fist creaks]
- You played like a joke today.
What the hell have you
been doing all this time?!
- Listen!
- He's a robot.
- The Human Metronome.
- Kid's nothing more
than his mother's puppet.
KOUSEI: They think I'm a robot,
but if I am, then...
- I ruined it for everyone!
- Well, that was
my chance at stardom.
[crossing bell ringing]
- [gasps]
- Hmm?
- Huh?
TSUBAKI: Hey! Kousei!
WATARI: Whoa! We got a live one!
- Why do I feel all this stuff?
What got through my armor?
- KOUSEI: Go.
- [panting]
- Go!
Go!
[screaming]
[train horn honks]
I'm the same
as Watari and Tsubaki
- and even you.
- [screaming]
I'm a person inside!
[Watari laughs] He's nuts.
TSUBAKI: Stop running!
[entry bell rings]
- Hey, I'm home.
- You look pretty happy.
I guess Arima did well, then.
- Disqualified. And great!
YOSHIYUKI: You know that
doesn't make sense, right?
- I'll explain later.
RYOUKO: Guess what, honey.
A letter came for you.
- Yeah? Curious.
I'm gonna get changed.
I'm all sweaty
from running around.
[pants]
[bed creaks]
[doorbell rings]
- [insects buzzing]
- [phone line ringing]
[doorbell rings]
- [gasps]
[shoes scraping]
[footsteps pattering]
[Hiroko gasps]
Oh, my God!
Kousei!
- [groans]
- Go for the head!
He's a freaking zombie!
- Where'd he go? Where'd he go?!
- Oh, hey. Good morning.
I'm glad to see you and all,
but why are you in my house?
- I'm here, 'cause somebody
wouldn't pick up the phone,
even though I called,
like, a billion times,
you punk!
[Kousei screams]
- [growls]
You didn't even change
out of your clothes,
you little slug.
Get your ass
to the bath, already.
You want me to give you one?
- Whoa!
- It wouldn't be the first time.
- [zipper unzips]
- No. I got it. I'm good.
Thanks for the offer,
but I'm gonna pass.
- [scoffs]
Nothing I haven't seen before.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Up all night playing the piano
'til he conked out.
KOUSEI: Hiroko.
[water splashing]
HIROKO: How 'bout that?
Maybe Kousei's not
all grown up yet.
[insects buzzing]
- Here you go, Ms.--
uh, Hiroko.
You take it black, right?
- At least you remember
the important stuff.
Hey, when's your dad
get back in town?
- Don't know.
- Yeah, that's about par
for the course.
- I've got some cold milk
if you'd like a glass.
- [whimpers]
- [chuckles]
She'll come around eventually.
[sips]
Tell you the truth,
I never thought I'd see the day
where you took up piano again.
- You and me both.
- So what prompted
this unlikely miracle?
- [chuckles]
[insects buzzing]
- [laughs]
- Summer vacation
is almost here.
- Achtung!
There will be no breaks
for us, Herr Friend A.
- Uh...
- Check it out,
an invite from Towa Hall.
I got it a few days ago.
- What kind of invite?
- Hey, that's the place
where Kousei backed you up
on the piano.
- This wouldn't have to
do
with their big gala
concert?
- Righto!
As I'm sure you know,
they hold concerts like this
every now and then
to commemorate something cool.
This time around,
they're having the recital
to honor the high level
of musicianship
displayed by the winners
and other top performers
at the Towa Music Competition.
- Gotcha.
- Huh?
So if music were like sports,
this would be
an exhibition match?
- A-plus, you!
- [gasps]
- Guess we did something right,
because the promoters really
want us to play their event.
That's me...
- and you.
- [gasps]
- Awesome! Looks like we're
getting the band back
together!
- I'm not gonna force you,
though.
[audience cheering]
It's your call.
[wind blowing]
[student chatter]
KOUSEI: Did you have
a particular song
in mind for the concert?
- Yep. Here. This one.
- Hmm?
- [metal bat rings]
But this is...
- Friedrich Kreisler.
It's his "Liebesleid."
- Meaning "Love's Sorrow."
SAKI: Kousei.
- And you're sure
you wanna play this?
These galas are usually a place
for people to show off,
and this one's really quiet.
- Shows what you know, mister.
I've given this matter
a ton of thought.
If everybody else is going big,
us taking the chill route
will make a splash.
Come on. I didn't roll in
off the turnip truck.
- Let's pick another,
something cooler maybe.
- I'm so sorry.
- [gasps]
- I never meant
to drop you like that,
and words don't
make up for it.
Forgive me.
Just grant me a little more
of your magic.
- She looks so delicate,
like she'd crumble to dust
if I touched her.
- All right.
Let's do it.
- [chuckles]
- So what prompted
this unlikely miracle?
- [sipping]
- This one day in April,
I met a violinist
as crazy as they come,
a total loose cannon,
and what a temper.
But when she smiles at you,
it's like she's an angel.
She punched and kicked
and cajoled me onto that stage.
And once I was finally there,
I saw something
that touched my soul.
I just--I know I want to see it
again, no matter what.
And since that's the goal,
I thought maybe I should
become a crazy pianist, right?
- [gasps]
Maybe.
- [grunting]
- Crazy! Crazy! Crazy!
- Okay, then.
- Crazy! Crazy!
- I'm gonna teach you
how to play.
- Huh?
- You don't gotta look
so scared about it.
- Sorry.
- [chuckles]
- Hiroko, I would be honored
to have you teach me.
[footsteps pattering]
- Look, slacker,
you gotta take this seriously.
- Who says that I'm not?
That was our first time
running the piece.
It's gonna get better.
- No excuses. Eh?
[laughing]
- Huh?!
- Just look at 'em!
Oh, wow.
Aren't they beautiful?
- Gotcha!
- Easy, now.
- [sighs]
It's so fragile and weak,
but look how bright it shines.
Thump, thump,
like a heartbeat.
["My Truth" playing]
This light is made
of life itself.
[clears throat]
Is this on?
- Eh?
- So, Friend A, how did
that competition treat you?
[giggles]
- [singing in Japanese]
- You know, I learned something
up on that stage.
Everyone has something
in their heart
that lets them
give the song their all.
For some, it takes
the form of anger.
Sometimes it's hope
or the need to be seen.
The thought let it reach them...
thoughts of a parent.
All of us brought a different
reason onto that stage.
Maybe you have to.
Maybe going out there
empty-handed just doesn't work.
- And you?
- [gasps]
- What did you have
in your heart up there?
What was your inspiration?
- [gasps]
I had you.
- [singing in Japanese]
KOUSEI: My journey, it's begun
to the roar of applause.
I pursue that magical moment
when my music reached them
and the magical soul
who leads me.
I know that someday
I'll walk alongside her
step for step.
Let's call it a night.
- [singing in Japanese]
- "You know...
I'm not always going to be
around to help you."
Charlie Brown.
["Kirameki" playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪