[ Audience murmuring ]
Huh?
[ Murmuring fades ]
[ Note chimes ]
[ Gasping ]
In that moment,
my fate was set.
[ playing
"Etude, Opus 25, Number 11" ]
MOTHER: Why'd you wanna come to
the park all of a sudden, Emi?
FATHER: Be careful.
You're really high up.
I'm Emi,
and I'm gonna play piano!
EMI:
On top of the jungle gym,
I pledged myself
to the life of a pianist.
[ Piano music continues ]
I set aside all other ambitions
for the sake of one.
Return to me.
OCHIAI:
Why, hello.
MOTHER:
She won't bite, honey.
A pleasure to meet you.
I'm Yuriko Ochiai.
Can you tell me your name?
I wanna...
Go on.
I wanna play
and make people who hear me
wanna play!
[ Whimpers ]
Can -- Can you make me good
at the piano like that?
I want it more than anything
in the world!
Return to me.
OCHIAI:
If you work hard enough, Emi,
I'm sure your music
will touch people, too.
The piano has a way
of listening.
Can I play it?
Of course you can.
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Note plays ]
[ Screams ]
That's the only kind of sound
I can make with it?
But when that boy was playing,
everything sounded
like sunflowers.
I just wanted to play
like you, Arima.
Every great performer
started out right where you are,
having never played before.
Even the likes of Mozart
and Beethoven were new once.
Whoever inspired you,
they went through
this same thing.
Now, my dear,
pretend the piano is a genie.
What would you wish for?
I want...
YOUNG EMI:
I wanna...
I wanna play the piano
like that boy did.
I want to stand
on the same stage as him.
Once I can play
as good as him...
...I'll see all those
sunflowers he shared with us.
[ "Etude, Opus 25, Number 11"
continues ]
Let it ring.
BOTH:
EMI:
Let it ring.
[ Exhales deeply ]
[ Audience cheering ]
Let it ring.
[ "Hikaru Nara" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Applause ]
TAKESHI:
Is that girl for real or what?
That was crazy just now.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
Well played.
That was great.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Huh?
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Listen, Arima!
Wait!
Is she confessing her love?
Sorry.
I'm gonna go change.
Yeah.
'Cause it is kind of chilly
back here.
[ Grunts ]
Come on!
EMI: Right now,
there's no need for words.
I said it all with my piano.
WOMAN: There will now be
an intermission.
Judging will resume
in 15 minutes.
[ Water running ]
You think there's something
wrong with that girl?
That was a bunch of pills
she just took.
Yeah.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Huh?
Hey, that girl's pretty hot.
You feeling okay, Tsubaki?
The closer we get
to Kousei's turn,
the more my stomach hurts.
I don't even get this nervous
before a softball game.
You've got the easy job
today.
You get to sit back and watch.
Just try to relax.
But I'm worried about Kousei.
I see a hot mom over there.
Bet you he's
freaking out right now.
That girl's performance
was amazing.
How's he supposed to come out
and play after that?
Give the guy
a little credit, yeah?
Kousei's gonna man up.
I know it.
[ Fingers tapping ]
WOMAN: Attention.
The competition
will now resume.
[ Heartbeat echoing ]
Oh, man. My heart.
It's pounding even harder
than it was before.
[ Heart beating ]
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
TAKESHI:
Arima's gonna play Chopin's
"Etude Opus 25,
Number 5" today,
but that song is way too easy.
What the hell?!
Back when he was competing,
Arima banked on his ability
to play difficult songs
to perfection.
Knowing that about him
was the whole reason
I chose "Winter Wind"
to be my piece today.
Takeshi knows it, too.
But the song that Arima
picked for this,
it's not difficult at all.
What's his angle, huh?
How'd you pick out
Kousei's song for today anyhow?
[ Chuckles ]
The pencil landed on 25-5!
You sealed my fate
with a pencil?!
Pencil!
Got it!
[ Laughs ]
He could play "Chopsticks"
for all that I care.
What matters is that he's here.
[ Music continues ]
Kousei's here,
and he's gonna play.
Kousei Arima?
You're the next one up.
Thank you.
Just being
in this recital hall,
it's waking up
a part of his soul.
I know he'll rise
to the occasion.
His rivals are out for blood,
and he can't ignore
that challenge.
He'll give it everything
he's got.
He will,
because Kousei's a musician.
Two years.
Has it really been that long?
My heart is pounding so hard,
like an animal
thrashing around.
Is it because I watched
those two play just now?
No holding back.
No safety net.
They poured their souls
into those pieces.
This is who I am!
Let it ring!
I'm the same as you.
Whatever stopped in him
that day,
it's about to start again.
Kaori?
[ Applause ]
I never noticed music
can have a color so vibrant,
even a smell.
Are you ready?
I know he's going to walk out
on that stage.
My blood is boiling,
and it's all because of music!
Go time.
WOMAN:
Hey, that's Arima.
MAN:
Really?
[ Footsteps echoing ]
Here we go.
I thought
I was nervous before,
but now --
Just hang in there, belly!
Huh?
[ Sighs ]
I'm guessing it's his turn.
[ Gasps ]
CAT: Are you ready
to go on your journey?
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
Wanna play dodgeball
with us?
I promise not to hit you
too hard.
Sorry, but...
I'm in the middle
of a piano lesson with Mom.
Again?
For reals?
Huh? What happened to your arm?
It's all bruised.
Oh, I knocked it into something,
but I'm okay.
You're, like, the clumsiest kid
I know.
SAKI: Kousei!
[ Gasps ]
You get back here right now!
That was super scary.
Mom's calling for me, Tsubaki.
I gotta go.
Maybe next time?
Okay.
Good luck with the piano.
Mm.
[ Music continues ]
Time to sit down, Kousei.
Come.
What are you waiting for?
Let's begin.
[ Gasps ]
KOUSEI:
[ Breathing heavily ]
WOMAN: No running in the halls,
please.
Sorry!
Hey, Mom! I brought you
some clean clothes from home.
Hey, Kousei.
Sorry I couldn't be there.
This was the big day, right?
Uh-huh.
I won first place.
Check out my certificate.
But Haydn's so tough for you.
That's why I practiced
a bunch.
That's a good boy.
I take a lot of pills,
but you spreading your wings
like this,
that's the best medicine
for me.
[ Sighs ] Then I'm --
I'm gonna keep coming in first
so you can keep feeling better
and better.
I'll get first
as many times as it takes.
I promise.
[ Heartbeat echoing ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
MAN: What's he doing?
WOMAN:
He's just standing there.
[ Audience murmuring ]
Don't be afraid.
You're fine.
[ Music continues ]
Damn it.
It's overpowering me.
It scares all of us.
[ Chord echoing ]
Now play.
Now play!
[ Playing "Etude Opus 25,
Number 5" ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
He's in the spotlight,
like he never left
in the first place.
He's returned,
the invincible pianist
in a league all his own,
the one I looked up to --
Kousei Arima.
Impeccable form.
He's perfect,
playing it exactly
as it's shown in the score.
And the music that results
might as well be a glacier.
Two years later,
nothing has changed.
I can hear the notes,
loud and clear.
I can play the score
exactly as I've memorized it.
Muscle memory will guide me
through this,
like riding a bike.
It's your entry.
How do you want to play it?
I'm playing
the way I always did.
SAKI:
That's how it should be.
Your job is to honor
the composer's vision,
not go on flights of fancy!
You know
that's the path to victory.
Now, then, are you
going to bring home
another first place
for your mother or aren't you?
[ Footsteps approaching ]
TSUBAKI: You were playing
the piano all day again, huh?
Yeah, but I had
to run to the store.
Dad's still away
on business,
so I had to make sure
me and Mom were good for food.
[ Laughs ]
What the...
All you bought
are egg sandwiches.
Get a little creative,
why don't you?
She won't let me use
the stove,
so there weren't
a lot of choices.
We've got some leftovers
from last night.
I'll bring 'em over for you,
okay?
Hey, Kousei, how's your mom
been feeling lately?
I heard my folks talking about
how she was still all sick
or something.
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
She told me she'd be going
into the hospital soon.
Really?
But how come?
All I know
is it's my fault.
Huh?
What'd you say?
Just forget it.
Mom wouldn't be so sick
if it weren't for me.
If I played how she told me,
this wouldn't have happened.
And so I'm gonna win
first place,
'cause she's sure
to get better then.
Arima won again?
[ Groans ] Leave it
to the Human Metronome.
[ Laughs ]
Just go to Europe already.
Bland and lifeless.
He's holding us back.
He's nothing but
his mother's puppet, anyway.
KOUSEI:
Shut up, all of you.
None of them know
what they're talking about.
It's me and my mom
versus everybody else.
Next time I perform,
my mom is gonna come
all the way from the hospital
to cheer me on.
Oh!
Really?
That must mean she's feeling
a lot better, then.
I'm so glad!
I guess that visit from me
raised her spirits, huh?
I did bring a gift.
Scented erasers
were kind of a random choice.
Up near the exit on
the left side of the audience,
somewhere I can see her.
Today that's my mom's
special seat.
I can't believe
she's really here.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And guess what, you guys.
I'm gonna play so well
while my mom is watching
that she'll feel
all the way better.
That way, she can finally
come home for good.
[ Audience cheering ]
[ Grunts ]
Saki, he's just a kid!
Your performance was garbage!
How many times have I told you
to review the goddamn score?!
How many times?!
You can't
just keep hitting him!
Oh, God.
But he played better today
than I'd ever seen before.
I'm going to go get
a staff member.
You played what you felt instead
of what was written down!
[ Gasps ]
[ Down-tempo music plays ]
You're not going to bed
until you play it right.
What are you, a damn beginner?
You're worthless!
I'm in the middle
of a piano lesson with Mom.
For reals?
You always ruin that part!
That kid's got bruises
all over him.
I bet you that's why he
always wears long sleeves.
So she hits her own son?
She's a monster.
[ Gasps ]
How dare you throw that score!
Pick it up now!
KOUSEI: All I wanted
was for you to be happy.
[ Gasps ]
Even when I just wanted
to play with my friends
or you hit me,
I sat back down at the piano
and kept practicing,
'cause I thought
if I did a good enough job
as a pianist, you'd get better.
[ Sobs ]
That's why I took all the pain.
To save you!
That's over now.
'Cause I don't care anymore.
Now I just wish you were dead.
[ Playing "Moonlight Sonata" ]
Those words were the last thing
I said to her...
ever.
[ Music continues ]
Hey, Kousei.
Yeah?
You gonna do the finals?
Uh-huh.
I made it through prelims, so...
[ Sighs ]
I know it's awful.
My mother just passed away,
and here I am
worrying about some competition
that's a few days later.
What kind of person
does that?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'll be fine.
After all, I'm doing
what Mom trained me to.
When I think back to that day,
I can't see her face.
[ Music continues ]
Nothing.
A black hole
staring back at me.
[ Music continues ]
His mother just died,
didn't she?
How can he play
like everything's fine?
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
He's not even off
by a fraction.
Like mother, like son.
[ Music continues ]
KOUSEI:
Up near the exit
on the left side
of the audience,
a spot where I could see her.
That was my mom's special seat.
And this...
this is my punishment.
[ Gasps ]
[ Heartbeat echoing ]
[ playing
"Etude, Opus 25, Number 11" ]
[ Heartbeat slows, fades ]
[ Music continues ]
SAKI: You're right.
This is punishment.
You deserve this.
You understand that,
don't you, my darling Kousei?
[ Wind blowing ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Off-key music playing,
keys thudding ]
The notes...
[ Gasps ]
What the...
The sound of the piano --
I've lost it.
He's unraveling.
That poor boy.
Can't even hear the notes
anymore, they say.
[ Music continues ]
[ Distorted music playing ]
[ Water bubbling ]
[ "Kirameki" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]