Tsubaki: Huh?!
How'd they get all broken?
I hid them
and everything.
Maybe they dried out
too much?
[ Whimpering ]
[ Crying ] I worked hard
to make them,
and now they're just dirt!
Don't cry, Tsubaki.
It's not the end of the world.
Shut up, Kousei!
Get out of here,
you big dummy!
Huh?
I don't care
if you leave me or not,
so just go away!
[ Crying ]
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
[ "Nanairo Symphony" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
-Morning.
-Oh, morning.
Young Woman: [ Laughs ]
Check out that tan.
Young Man: I lost my whole
summer to cram school.
-So you ready?
-Readyish.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Kousei: I'd like to test
for Okutsu College's
high school prep track.
Teacher: That's in
another prefecture, right?
Yes, but my dad says
he's okay with it.
My moving, that is.
The best conservatories
are picky.
It all comes down
to your competition record
and who you've trained with,
so it might not pan out.
[ Gasps ]
That said, my mentor
thinks going overseas
might be a good fit.
I guess there's a friend she
wants me to meet from the time
she spent abroad.
[ Growling ]
Thinking of the big picture.
That's good.
Stupid friend-napping Hiroko!
Best of luck.
Thank you.
[ Gasps ]
♪♪
Go ahead. Move away.
Go to the Moon,
for all I care.
You dummy. I don't care
if you're with me or not,
so just go away!
If you don't care
if I'm with you or not...
[ Gasps ]
[ Stammering ]
[ Groans ]
[ Groaning ]
If you're trying
to keep it bottled up,
it's not working out.
We're not even counting
this one, right?
I can read you
like a book.
We could have had
a new school record here.
Hmm?
[ Sputtering ]
Hope you had a good trip!
Even I'm not
that clumsy.
Well, been nice
knowing you two.
Target acquired.
[ Boys wail ]
Watari:
I'm too cute to die!
[ Indistinct conversations ]
I think
I peed a little.
Hmm.
Is it me,
or has she been
acting kind of weird?
Oh, it's you, alright.
I would just leave her alone
for a bit.
Well, excuse me
for falling on my face.
It hurts, you know.
Laughing like you haven't
got a care in the world.
Would a compliment
kill you?
I'd have to move.
Whenever I talk to you,
I feel better,
or I feel worse.
I'm such a mess right now.
Pretty lame, huh?
[ Grunts ]
[ Kids gasp ]
[ Yelling ]
Kids:
That's crazy!
Tsubaki.
They just look that way
'cause you're Bigfoot!
You think if you say it
enough times,
you'll convince everyone,
including yourself.
You're too chicken
to face the facts.
♪♪
[ Kids laughing ]
Uh...
Saito, I--
So, hey,
there's this one girl
at school.
Huh?
An upperclassman.
Met her, 'cause she's manager
of the baseball team.
She's got long hair,
and she's really down to
earth,
kind of girly, eats her chips
with chopsticks.
It's just we're
way too much alike.
You know what
I'm talking about.
Think about it.
We're both infielders,
and we've got short hair,
and we're both kind of blunt.
♪♪
And when you're with me,
you always seem like you
want to be somewhere else.
You laugh, but it's
like the nervous kind.
Me and you...
we should be
with those quiet types, right?
Huh? Saito.
I didn't...
It's not like the end
of the world or anything.
We just didn't work out.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, Saito.
[ Crying ]
I'm sorry.
[ Grunts ]
Hey,
what's the big idea
telling me sorry
over and over?
I'm the one
who's breaking up with you.
Really, though,
thank you
for being my girlfriend
and all.
[ Slowly playing
"Clair de lune" ]
♪♪
Hey.
Scoot over a bit.
I've got to practice,
you know.
I'm scooting!
Just hold your horses.
I thought I heard the piano
making some weird sounds.
Mystery solved.
'Scuse me, Mozart.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Playing "Clair de lune" ]
♪♪
Are you gonna
ask me about it?
No,
but I'm listening.
♪♪
I just got dumped.
This older boy
that I had a crush on,
really cute
and a good guy.
I guess
he was kind of like
a package
of that fancy ice cream,
the kind you never buy,
because it's too expensive...
the kind
people go crazy about.
The kind that's
not my style.
Said he liked me.
I was thrilled,
so I went for it.
And now it's over.
The worst part is...
[ Crying ]
I really hurt him.
I'm such an idiot.
How come I didn't know
what was in my heart?
I wish
I still didn't know.
I'd give anything for life
to go on the way it always has.
But...
Well, that was
my chance at stardom.
I'd like to test
for Okutsu College's
high school prep track.
Tsubaki: Time is moving forward
for Watari...
and Kousei.
Even when they
can't see what's coming,
even when they're afraid,
they still go on...
one foot in front of the other,
they find the courage
to keep moving,
supporting each other,
inspiring each other,
working as a team.
They're on their way,
and I'm stuck.
I was right
about time stopping...
but the only one
who got frozen was me.
[ Crying ]
Are you gonna play
that stupid song all night,
or are you gonna
comfort me, already?!
"Clair de lune" can wait,
you big jerk!
I'm hurting here!
I don't care if you're
with me or not, so go!
[ Sniffles ]
Alright.
If you don't care
if I'm with you or not...
Then I'll just stay.
You're stuck with me.
[ Gasps ]
What the hell's
wrong with you!
Quit it!
You can't be super nice
to a girl
right after she gets dumped!
[ Playing "Clair de lune" ]
♪♪
It's not like I was being
extra nice to you,
just boring old me.
Right by my side
whenever I was hurting,
anytime I was sad,
like a brother to me, but not.
Young Kousei:
You're stuck with me.
Liar.
Even now,
you're getting ready to leave.
Maybe it's too late, but...
I'm not giving up.
I'm just a jock
and one of the guys,
and I don't know anything
about the piano,
but I finally know what I want.
Honestly, I hate music.
It's always taking
Kousei away from me.
[ Chuckles ]
Would you look at that?
The moon is out.
[ Crying ]
Yeah. So what?
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
It's pretty.
Maybe so.
Dummy. Don't be so nice.
It just makes it hurt worse.
♪♪
There's the mark.
It's now or never.
Time for this ice...
to thaw.
[ Piano playing ]
♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Bravo! Amazing!
What a talent.
I'll never accuse you
of teaching the boring ones,
Ms. Ochiai.
I find young talent
so volatile.
They burn all the brighter
when faced with one another.
[ Chuckles ]
Be a dear,
and thank the boy for me.
I'm right behind you, Arima.
No...
don't look back.
Move ahead. Give it your all.
You'll see me soon enough
as I pass you.
[ Cheering continues ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Siren wails ]
[ Grunts ] Come on!
All you're doing is visiting her
in the hospital!
It's nothing
to freak out about, Kousei!
[ Gasps ] A crow?!
And a black cat?!
Not happening.
[ Crow caws ]
Now probably wasn't
a good time, anyway.
Somebody's a big chicken.
Soon as there's some distance,
it gets harder to see you,
even though we spent all sorts
of time practicing together,
I'm looking
for reasons to visit
and reasons
to keep putting it off.
[ Wails ]
[ Sputters ] Huh?
[ Gasps ]
A freakin' water balloon!
Konnyaku?!
And a bucket?!
I knew today was unlucky.
[ Girl chuckles ]
Did you like that?
There's more
on the way.
[ Meows ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screams ]
[ Kousei groans ]
I give up.
Hiroko: You know
mi casa es su casa,
but if you bring a girl over,
have some class.
Don't just lug her in
like a bag of burgers.
Come on.
It's nothing like that!
Has he brought
a bag of burgers?
I want one!
[ Groaning ]
She's awake.
Thank goodness.
[ Stammers ]
Where am I?
You sure know
how to pick 'em, Kousei.
Hey, kid,
you fainted out there,
so he brought you home
like a sack of hamburgers.
That isn't what happened!
You totally carried her in.
Koharu: Mommy, where are
the burgers? I'm hungry!
Pardon me for asking,
but could you possibly be
Hiroko Seto?
Who wants to know?
I should introduce myself.
I'm a first year
at Kurumi-Gaoka Junior High.
My name is Nagi Aizato.
Their music program
is top-notch.
You a musician?
Yes. Yes, I am,
as a matter of fact.
I want to be a pianist.
What's an aspiring pianist
doing up in a tree?
Honestly, I'm one
of your biggest fans, Ms. Seto,
so please take me on
as a student!
-Huh?
-I beg of you!
Uh, I don't usually go
for the hard sell, kiddo.
Plus it's kind of
a slap in the face
to your current teacher, right?
Tell you what.
If this is something
you really want to pursue,
go show me what you got.
Alright, then.
Your posture's good,
so that's a plus.
What are you going to play?
Maybe a little Bach?
No, Chopin's
"Etude Opus 25, Number 5."
[ Gasps ]
That was Kousei's piece
at the Maihou Competition.
[ Breathes deeply ]
[ Playing
"Etude Opus 25, Number 5" ]
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
She's good.
♪♪
The notes are all there,
but why does it
sound so harsh?
♪♪
A song like this.
That was really pretty!
Your music program
is no slouch.
Are all the first years
playing like that nowadays?
Wow,
and after fainting, no less.
Was that,
you know, good enough?
Hmm.
Alright.
[ Gasps ]
[ Crying ]
Thank you so much!
You don't
got to cry about it.
I can't believe
I'm gonna get piano lessons
from the Hiroko Seto!
Mission accomplished.
She's so happy.
Hey, Kousei.
Uh-huh.
You don't mind
teaching her, right?
[ Gulps ]
Huh?!
[ Meows ]
Clerk: Thank you very much.
[ Entry bell chimes ]
Alright, no black cats
or crows this time.
Plus I got her a gift.
If I don't see her,
they'll just go stale.
Yeah.
Of course I'd drop by
for a visit.
I'm her accompanist.
That's what you do.
Coming or going, I'm always
looking for a good excuse.
Watari: So he's totally soaked
from head to toe, right.
[ Kaori laughs ]
Nakamura starts laughing
so hard that snot
just rockets out of his nose.
Gross!
So I start busting up, too,
and, boom, more snot!
[ Both laugh ]
Canelés?
Her parents own a bakery.
It's a good thing
I didn't actually go in.
I'm such an idiot.
[ Cat meowing ]
♪♪
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Yelps ]
No name?
Kaori: You're a big old jerk!
You know that?!
Watari always
comes to visit me!
But Friend A
just can't be bothered.
What a butt-head!
Huh?
Wait a sec.
How did you even get my number?
I realized I hadn't
heard your dumb voice
for a while, so --
You were eating
something sweet, weren't you?
Yeah, a canelé.
Lucky! I wish
I could have a canelé.
[ Sighs ]
How about
I bring you some?
No kidding?
You promise you'll do it?
Yeah.
You remind me of a cat.
When I reach out to you,
you turn tail
and run off in a huff.
But when you're hurt,
you get playful,
like you haven't
a care in the world.
You're contrary,
and I love that about you.
Actually, can you grab me
my Dad's canelés?
[ Grunts ]
Cross your heart?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know why,
but canelés at night,
they taste better somehow.
Yeah. [ Sighs ]
Totally called it.
I knew her face looked familiar
from somewhere.
Hmm.
♪ Nous, nous canelé ♪
♪ Canelé pour nous ♪
Ohh! [ Grunts ]
[ Sighs ]
I fell.
[ Panting ]
What the...
[ Gasping ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Sliding ]
[ Grunting, groaning ]
[ Panting ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Yells ]
Stupid legs! Stand up!
You're supposed to do
what I say,
so stand up, already!
What are you waiting for?!
Stand up!
[ Crying ]
[ Screams ]
[ "Orange" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪