[ Tsubaki sneezes ]
[ Sniffles ]
Boy:
Tsubaki caught a cold?
That she-gorilla who wears
shorts all year long?
Girl:
She sneezes funny.
We're already infected!
-We need a medic!
-Run!
Girl: She's gonna
gorillafy us!
Tsubaki: Who are you calling
a gorilla, you little twerps?
Kid:
It's on the warpath!
[ Sneezes ]
Kousei: Here.
Have some lemonade.
Huh? What are you doing?
Vitamin C's good to take
when you have a cold.
My mom told me so.
Yeah? Well, I don't have a cold,
so there.
Gorillas are healthy
all the time.
You're not a gorilla
at all, Tsubaki.
Huh?
You're a human.
A human girl.
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Vitamin C!
Whoa!
[COALAMODE.'S
"Nanairo Symphony"]
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Girl: Happy New Year!
You, too.
Boy: I was cramming
all through --
Boy #2: I think I'm gonna try
for an easier school.
Girl #2:
I missed you!
Girl #3: I heard he got
early admission.
Boy #3:
Must be nice.
[ Girl giggles ]
Read them and weep!
B again!
-Love, right?
-Got to be love.
Girl #4:
No doubt about it.
Tsubaki: See what you can do
when you put your mind to it?
[ Laughs ]
I should go tell him!
[ Door sliding open ]
Oh, Kousei?
Aww.
Hey!
Not today, buddy.
Come here.
The lovely Kaori requests
your presence within.
Kousei: I'm just gonna be
the third wheel.
This is a horrible idea,
Watari.
Happy New Year!
Right back at you!
You know, just because you
squeaked through the prelims
doesn't mean you can rest
on your laurels,
and waste time
at the hospital!
Go home and practice,
you slacker!
Kousei:
You're the one that told me
to stop by in the first place.
Watari: Remember that kid
I mentioned?
Mm-hmm.
They're sending her off
to an all-girls school.
I'd totally go to
a school like that.
You'd have to wear
the uniform.
We could be roomies,
partners in crime.
Yeah -- till they kick
both of us out.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Tsubaki: She's totally
interested in Watari.
Kaori: [ Laughs ]
Watari!
Kousei: The girl who likes
my best friend.
I'm just a third wheel,
and a stand-in,
and a pack mule,
and her accompanist
all too briefly.
But I'm not Watari.
[ Cicadas chirping ]
Hey, are you sure?
I don't think your mom's
gonna like it.
That just means
I'll have to do
whatever it takes
to keep her.
How could Mom say "no"
to something this cute?
It's gonna be fine.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
[breathing heavily]
♪♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
Tsubaki: Drink it.
You're gonna catch a cold
if you don't warm up, Kousei.
I've been looking
for Chelsea everywhere,
but she's not at the junkyard
or under the bridge.
She's gonna freeze to death
out in the rain.
She's just
a little kitten!
I let my mom
take her away,
even though I knew she'd
never give Chelsea back.
But I thought, if I
could find her out here,
at least I'd know
she was alright!
Girl:
He's his mother's puppet.
Boy:
The human metronome.
Kousei: It's true what
they say about me!
I'm a soulless puppet
my mom created
because she can't play
the piano anymore!
[ Crying ]
Shows what you know.
I bet your soul is
all kinds of shiny.
Seriously, Kousei.
You're a lot
of good things.
You've just got to
remember them.
Yeah, like the way...
uh...
Well, like the way
you're out here
looking for Chelsea
in the rain.
It's 'cause you feel bad
about what happened to her.
Puppets wouldn't feel
that kind of stuff, right?
See, Kousei?
You do, too, have a soul.
It's just that you
put it away somewhere,
and now, you don't remember
exactly where it is.
That's why I'll find
your soul for you.
It'll be a big job,
and it might take me a while.
Even after we find it,
I'll stay with you
forever and ever.
How's that sound?
[ Rain pattering ]
Going to the hospital?
-Yeah.
She demands that I check in
with her a bunch,
then yells at me for not
using the time to practice.
I can't win.
Watari.
I bet you he's heading over
to see Kaori, too.
Actually,
I think it's gonna rain.
Let's go another day.
It does smell rainy.
Oh?
Check it out, Kousei.
You called it.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
Here.
You read my mind.
Now, if you could just
turn this all into snow.
Yeah, 'cause trudging
to school through it
is so much fun.
Pour some syrup
into it,
and you can make
your own shaved ice.
If people weren't weird
about yellow snow,
we could use
that lemonade.
We're just
like always --
making silly jokes,
hiding out from the rain.
I like your handkerchief,
Tsubaki.
It's cute.
The two of us,
him and me.
It's pretty girly,
but you are a girl.
You're a human.
A human girl.
I guess you're a girl
after all, huh?
You liar.
♪♪
I know why you backed out
on going to see Kaori.
It's 'cause
of Watari.
Kousei: No. It looked rainy.
That's all.
You're lying.
♪♪
Honestly, I didn't want
to get in the way
if they had the chance
to be alone.
Just stop it!
The only reason we're here
is 'cause watching them laugh
and have fun,
it tears you up inside!
♪♪
That's why you avoid her.
Kousei: I can tell right away
when you're holding back.
You think you can keep it
all bottled up,
but I've always known
what's in your heart.
I can read you like a big,
dumb book.
♪♪
You love Kaori.
You've loved her
all along.
Kaori:
Miwa told me something.
The moment I
laid eyes on him,
my old life
just blew away.
Everything I saw and heard,
everything I felt,
the world around me
took on color
in a way
I never knew it could.
It began to sparkle.
You're Friend A!
Mm-hmm.
[ Rain pattering ]
Well, it's not
gonna happen, okay?
Kaori's all head over heels
for Watari.
Always has been,
dummy.
As if she'd ever give you
a second look.
Yeah, I know.
When it comes to girls,
you're not gonna beat him.
Next to him,
they wouldn't even see you.
You're right.
You liar.
You told me
you'd stay with me.
Kousei: I can tell right away
when you're holding back.
You've known me forever,
but you can't tell
what I'm feeling,
can you?
I'm not even a girl
to you, huh?
You've never
seen me as one.
[ Somber music plays ]
Stop acting
like a moron.
Kaori likes him.
That's just how it is.
♪♪
[ Exhales ]
Maybe...
You should fall in love
with me instead.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
Whatever, you dummy!
See, Kousei?
That's what truth sounds like.
It was scary, but at least
he gets the picture, now,
that I'm a girl.
It took a lot of tears
to get here.
Bet you he's crying, too --
not 'cause of his feelings,
but because I kicked him
so hard.
He knows.
I told him.
But what happens now?
My heart's
a mile a minute.
The rain feels so good,
and it tastes like lemonade.
I was frozen before,
but I just started to thaw.
[ Gasps ]
Hey, Tsubaki.
Kashiwagi: Thanks for
waiting.
[ Somber music plays ]
[ Baseball bat clinks ]
♪♪
Look, you have a cold,
and I'm tired.
Let's call it
a day, yeah?
[ Coughing ]
I just got rained on
a bit.
Now, keep those
pitches coming.
Fine.
But you're bringing them
all back from now on.
If that's what
I got to do.
♪♪
Something happen
with you and Arima?
[ Gasps, shouts ]
[ Screams ]
[ Clattering ]
Are you trying to
knock my head off?
What the hell?
You can't just say stuff
like that mid-pitch!
Come on.
I wasn't born yesterday.
Each ball is landing
by the music room.
You're fighting again.
Am I right?
No.
Though I did kick him
in the leg pretty hard,
I guess.
Now that I
think about it,
he was limping
a little.
Hey, I didn't want to
talk about it
in the first place, okay?
I just wanted to hit
some balls around!
You are officially
on my bad list!
Suffer, Kashiwagi!
Not my fault you're
crazy for him.
Now that you know
I'm a girl, Kousei,
think of me.
[ Baseball bat clinks ]
Reach him.
You can do it!
♪♪
You should fall in love
with me instead.
Kousei: I mean,
what was that even about?
She was just
messing around.
But Tsubaki doesn't
joke like that.
Tsubaki: It's like having
a hopeless kid brother.
Kousei:
Girls are weird --
even the ones
you've known forever.
[ Ominous moaning ]
Woman:
Focus, damn it!
You've got to get your head
in the game, pal!
The finals were in February,
for crying out loud!
Sorry about that.
I'd like to say that
he's ahead of the pack,
but I'd be lying.
His head is
in the back?
Listen to me.
You'll be pitting
your skills against
the top young pianists
in Japan.
Whether you're going on
to high school here,
or bugging out
for Europe,
this competition
will decide your future.
It's time to sack up.
You're playing in
the big leagues now.
Kaori: I'm releasing you
from visit duty.
Huh?
The finals are right
around the corner.
Time for you to put every
spare moment into practice.
An hour here,
an hour there,
it adds up.
Anyway, I got to go.
Talk to you later!
[ Phone receiver clicks ]
[ Phone beeping ]
[ Groans ]
What is her problem?
First she
demands I visit,
then she gives me
crap about it,
and now, she tells me
not to bother!
Which is it, tyrant?!
Kousei: Maybe it was
something I did.
I knew I shouldn't have eaten
her caneles that one time.
And I definitely don't talk
enough while I'm there.
She might still be steamed
about the Nagi thing, too.
If I don't see her
in the hospital,
does that mean I won't get
a chance to see her at all?
[ Cellphone ringing]
[shouts]
[ Cellphone buzzes ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
You again?
Kaori: I looked out the window,
and saw this huge plane.
I wonder where
it's going?
Cool, huh?
Huh?
Yeah, there it goes.
Kaori: Hold on.
You can see it, too?
Wow, I guess we're under
the same sky.
Is that why you called?
Yeah.
Is that okay?
[ Laughing ]
The plane set sail
across an ocean of stars.
Like a cat in the dark,
you appear out of nowhere.
You told me not to come
to the hospital.
It doesn't mean I'm not
gonna call, silly.
I had to share that plane
with someone.
Just when I'm sure
she's through with me,
there she is, beckoning
for me to follow her.
Same as I've always done.
I'll stop in
to see you.
You really
don't have to.
It'd be different
if you had the time, but --
I don't care
about time.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
I want to see you.
It flies overhead
as though by magic.
Knowing I'm under
the same sky as you,
it paints the night
with a touch of wonder.
You speak, and I swing
between hope and despair,
keeping time to the melody
in my heart.
What do people call
this feeling, again?
Something so rare
must have a name.
Maybe they call it
"being in love."
That okay?
Even if they don't,
I know I do.
Watari: I got the school thing
figured out.
Kousei: Oh, yeah?
How'd you do it?
One of them offered me
a soccer scholarship,
so I took the bait.
They told me to start
hitting up practice in March.
Bottom of the heap
again, man.
Circle of life.
Still surprised
you came with.
When I'd ask before,
you'd always weasel out of it.
It wasn't you.
I'm no Watari.
I'm the first to admit it.
But it still hurts.
Tsubaki:
You love Kaori.
You've loved her
all along.
Kaori: You see?
You're just yourself.
Hey, Watari.
♪♪
I like Kaori --
like, a lot.
♪♪
Well, yeah.
Of course you do.
[ Laughs ]
So, are we gonna duke it out
for her, or what?
Nurse: Get the doctor
in here now!
That's Kaori's room.
Just hang on.
The doctor's on his way.
Kaori, can you hear me?
Nurse #2:
Take a deep breath, Kaori.
That's a good girl.
Deep breaths.
Nurse #3: We need the doctor
in here! Find him!
Kaori!
Look at me!
Damn it,
she's seizing up!
Patient is coding!
You have to keep
your eyes open, Kaori!
Kaori!
Doctor:
You can't be here right now.
Go home, boys.
We'll take
good care of her.
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪♪
[ Tires squealing ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪♪
Kousei: Hello?!
Please open up!
I need help!
[ Gasping ]
♪♪
Doctor: Prep it for X-ray,
and check its blood type.
♪♪
I wish I could have
done more,
but with injuries that bad,
they're beyond help.
I'm sorry.
Thank you
for trying.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
[ Distant dog barking ]
[ Water running ]
Kaori: Do you think
you can just forget it?
You should come along.
Your hand is ready
to jump out of its skin.
I'm glad it was you.
[ Crying ]
[ Screams ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Singing continues ]
♪♪