[ Playing "Love's Sorrow" ]
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Door opens ]
[ Playing stops ]
[ Sighs ] Please.
You know darn well
I'm gonna say yes.
[ Sighs ]
♪ Hubby is a dummy ♪
♪ So watch your ass,
honey ♪
♪ Or I'mma kick you out ♪
[ Humming melody ]
Hiroko,
did you and your husband
get in another fight?
[ Scoffs ]
This is no mere fight.
It's way more epic
than that.
If he doesn't say sorry,
we're splitsville.
Oh.
♪ Hubby is a dummy ♪
♪ Watch your ass,
honey ♪
♪ Or I'mma kick you out ♪
What the -- Kousei.
How are you
doing that?
Hmm?
I just play,
same as you.
[ Gasps ]
Hiroko: Saki!
Now you've got to
make him a pianist!
Listen to me.
Your little boy is a genius!
[ "Nanairo Symphony" playing ]
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Audience murmuring ]
Kousei:
Well, it's time.
Wait.
By yourself?
Yeah.
You're serious?
I am.
[ Sighs ]
Well, what are you
going to play?
Without the violin,
it doesn't --
I'm keeping our song.
Huh?
When she plays, it's nothing
more than a bunch of noise.
Miike threw down
the gauntlet,
so I am picking it up.
I'll prove she's great,
with or without her.
[ Sighs ]
Besides...
I think Her Highness
will get a kick out of this.
I mean, she did want our song
to stand out today.
[ Applause ]
Today's a violin concert, right,
so what's the deal?
Does he mean
to play it on his own?
This is all
your fault, you know?
You're the one
who pushed me back onstage.
Even now,
I feel you under my skin.
I want this.
More than ever.
More than anything.
And so do I!
Hmm.
[ Gasps ]
Time to prove it,
that I'm incredible.
And if she chose me
to accompany her,
that means she's even better.
[ Playing "Love's Sorrow" ]
Thumbing his nose
at convention yet again!
Damn that Arima!
This is more
than just half a duet.
"Love's Sorrow,"
Rachmaninoff's
piano arrangement,
and he's playing it
from memory.
[ "Love's Sorrow" continues ]
♪♪
Saki adored that song.
All these years,
it's echoed in you, but...
your mom never
infused the notes
with so much frustration.
♪♪
Kousei: Watch me.
Don't you dare look away.
See how good I am?
Well, my partner
is even better!
Look at him go.
He's so passionate.
[ Sighs ]
What a letdown.
He's throwing a tantrum
at the keys.
This brute force is a far cry
from true ferocity.
It's so grating.
[ Distorted music playing ]
[ Keys pounding ]
Hold on. The keys,
how hard am I pounding them
right now?
My spine is taut as piano wire.
This is a mess.
[ Bubbles popping ]
It's not right.
This isn't how it's
supposed to sound.
I heard her play it
a thousand times.
She'd lull me off
to sleep with it.
I don't get it.
[ Tones thumping ]
Nothing has changed.
I can't hear my piano
for the life of me...
[ Tones thumping ]
but I can hear what's inside.
All it means is that
you're not limited
to whatever your ears
are picking up.
Haven't you ever felt them
soaking into
those muted notes you play?
[ Gasps ]
Don't think of it
as a handicap.
Losing your notes,
it might be a gift.
Saki: Kousei.
Play it more gently.
Touch it like you're
holding a little baby.
Just like
how I used to hold you.
[ Sighs ]
Mom.
If you were here,
how would you play it?
I-I think I know.
♪♪
Ochiai: The difference
is night and day.
Emi: Suddenly the sound,
it's changing.
♪♪
Kousei.
[ Chuckles ]
Huh?
It's Saki.
I can hear her.
[ Sighs ]
Hiroko: Saki!
You have got to get
your act together!
You just hit your son
until he bled!
You know that, right?
What kind of a mom
does that?!
What did he do?
What has he ever done,
except try
and make you happy?!
Don't you think
I see that, Hiroko!
Saki!
♪♪
He does his best.
But...
[ Crying ]
I'm out of time.
This is all I can be.
I know.
[ "Love's Sorrow" continues ]
♪♪
[ Kousei crying ]
Help me.
Please help me.
Somebody help me.
The notes on the piano...
where did they go?
They're gone.
I can't hear them.
Somebody, somebody, help me.
Mom.
[ Sighs ]
Kousei.
I'm the one that tossed you
into the deep end.
She didn't want
to make you a pianist,
but I pushed her.
I'm sorry.
If all that Kousei
gets out of music
are pain and suffering...
Forgive me.
...then I should go.
I've screwed up his life
enough already.
I didn't know.
Hiroko: But now...
[ Crying ]
our Kousei is back.
So what prompted
this unlikely miracle?
Kousei: I just--
I know I want to see it again,
no matter what.
And since
that's the goal,
maybe I should become
a crazy pianist, right?
[ Gasps ]
Hiroko:
Years after he lost his mother,
he finds a girl
who means everything to him.
It's not a lot to go off of,
but if it's enough to bring him
back to the land of the living,
then, damn it, I believe.
♪♪
Saki, you don't want
to miss this.
I know it's a little late,
but he's finally ready
to say goodbye.
♪♪
Kousei: Huh.
This song brings back
memories of her.
I even remember
how she used to smell.
When you play,
who's your song intended for?
Will it reach her?
I hope it does.
Saki:
What's he going to do...
after I'm gone?
Can he make a life
of this?
[ Sobs ] Tell me I've taught
him
that much, at least.
There was no time
for the art of it.
All I could do was force him
to play exactly what's
written.
So long as
he can do that,
maybe the piano
will support him someday.
What a terrible mother...
leaving her baby
all alone like this.
I wonder, will he remember
to brush his teeth?
He falls asleep
anywhere.
What if
he catches a cold?
He'll want
to play sports later.
What if
he hurts himself?
I wish that...
we could have had
more time together.
Kousei,
my little treasure,
will you ever
find happiness?
♪♪
I should have known.
The ghost of my mother
was a shadow I created...
my weakness personified
and my guilt.
Mom isn't out there
judging me from afar.
She's here.
She's a part of me.
Yes, of course.
The piano...
you don't play it.
You embrace it.
♪♪
Young Kousei: Hey, Mom,
tell me something.
If there's a song
called "Love's Joy"
and one called
"Love's Sorrow,"
how come you always
just play the second one?
[ Gasps ]
I play it...
[ Chuckles ]
...so that sorrow
won't be as scary.
Hiroko: Nobody's alone
in this life.
We're all notes
in one big coloratura,
wholes, halves, quarter notes.
Music connects us
with the people we know
and with the people we don't...
all the people in the world.
♪♪
Kaori: You should come along.
Kousei: I'm connected to Kaori,
and I'm connected to Mom.
Now that I know that much,
I can move forward.
So...
so...
♪♪
goodbye.
[ Music ends ]
[ Bench scrapes ]
[ Footsteps echoing ]
[ Applause ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Footsteps echoing ]
Goodbye.
[ Gasps ]
[ Footsteps echoing ]
[ Thump ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Shudders ]
I got weak in the knees.
Guess that took a lot out of me.
Huh?
Hiroko: Kousei!
Kousei!
[ Grunts ]
[ Wails ]
[ Crying ]
[ Hiroko chuckles ]
Can't call you
Mr. Quitter today.
She's throwing herself
at boys already?
I see gray hair
in my future.
[ Koharu murmuring ]
[ Gasps ]
Your mom, you saw her?
She's with me...
always.
I know that now.
Yeah.
I reach for the keys
the same way she did.
I press the pedals
the same way.
The things that I like,
even how I eat...
It's like she lives on
in every little thing
that I do.
My mom and I,
we're connected.
[ Sighs ]
Hiroko, do you think
it reached her?
[ Crying ]
I played the song
as well as I could.
Do you think
that my mom could hear it?
[ Crying ]
Dummy. You just told me
you're connected, right?
You can bet your ass
she did.
[ Sobbing ]
♪♪
Kousei: Thanks to music,
I've met people
I never would have known.
And every person that I've met,
they've changed me somehow.
What brought me back to life...
you gave me this.
a heart full of memories
I only possess
because you taught me
to play the piano.
I'm happy, Mom.
I really am.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
-Wow, that was exquisite.
-Wow.
Man: Really, I could
just go home now.
[ Applause ]
Man #2: Oh, right.
There's one left.
I don't think
I'm ready for more.
Miike: I've never been so scared
to go out onstage before.
Unfortunate.
That's a tough act
to follow.
I want to run away.
[ Gasps ]
Mom.
Could I have played
my heart out like he did?
with as much sincerity?
Maybe--
Maybe I can give it my all
like Arima.
One way to find out.
Watch me.
[ Playing "Violin Sonata
in E minor, Opus 82" ]
Right now, all I want
is to hear my Mom's voice.
-[ Gasping ]
-What?
That's a bit pianissimo
for Miike.
I see. You weren't
immune to it, either.
Arima's piece,
it's raising the bar.
♪♪
[ Crowd murmuring ]
Ah,
that was amazing!
All in all,
a fine concert.
You know...
Hmm?
I think being a musician's
the best.
[ Chuckles ]
Conquering an evil foe,
there's nothing like it
in the whole world.
That's what she likes
about it?
There he is,
dead ahead,
the man of the hour!
Hey! [ Laughs ]
Kousei, you --
[ Heart beats ]
Huh?
What the...
This is so weird.
It's like I don't
know what to say.
Freaky.
You sure
you don't got to stick around?
Nah, it's fine.
I came out here to play,
and that's what I did.
And now...
time to track down
little Miss No-show
and find out
why she bailed on me!
He's really mad.
Yeah. You think?
Let's call it a day.
I'm wiped out,
you guys.
I want a juice box.
Hmm. Cut me in for some,
and you got yourself a deal.
[ Laughs ]
Kousei: Tsubaki.
Hey, you're being
awfully quiet there.
So what did you think?
Well, I think...
you look pretty grown-up.
[ Laughs ]
I mean my playing.
Would a compliment
kill you?
[ Gasps ]
What?
What the heck?
You weirdo.
How come I feel like...
I'm gonna start crying?
What for?
Are they tears of relief
'cause we talk
like nothing was different?
Or tears of regret
because...
[ Drops echoing ]
...I really hoped it would be?
[ Insects buzzing ]
[ Playing "Nocturne in D-flat
Major, Opus 27, Number 2" ]
♪♪
It wouldn't have
killed you to come up
and say hello to me
at the concert, you know.
That said, you keeping
your distance at the show
was classic Ochiai.
[ Sighs ] I admit
I was surprised
to hear you're mentoring
the boy, and with good reason.
After all, you made yourself
right scarce
after poor Saki
passed away.
[ Sighs ]
You're not the only one
who's changed.
It's clear
he's evolving as a pianist.
Yeah.
He's taking
what's inside him
and playing it
for all to hear.
I think...
he's finally moving forward
as an honest-to-God artist.
[ Insects buzzing ]
[ Hiroko sighs ]
Look, losing Saki
was a tragedy.
It damn near
shattered me,
and I know for a fact
it shattered him.
Sure, it forced him
to grow as a musician.
Fair enough, but that's one hell
of a price to pay.
[ Sighs ]
Ochiai:
Everything Arima plays now
is tinged with a quiet sorrow.
If his growth as of late
was set into motion
by his mother's death, then...
I fear he's on a painful path.
[ Insects buzzing ]
And if he means
to tread this path...
the day might
eventually come...
[ Buzzing fades ]
...when the muses
demand another loss.
[ "Orange" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪