- Takeshi,
you've received an invitation
from the Schuberstein
Competition.
Congratulations. You're
finally heading to Europe.
It'll conflict with the Maihou,
but we can cancel that one.
- Tell 'em I can't, then.
- Hmm?
- Europe.
It's gonna have to wait.
- What?
- I want to enter
the Maihou Competition.
- [gasps]
What do you mean?
You got an overseas invitation.
Do you know how rare
those chances are?
The Chopin Competition is soon,
and you need international
exposure before then.
Besides, you won the Maihou
last year, Takeshi.
There's no reason
for you to do this.
- There is a reason, okay?
Kousei Arima
might be competing this time.
- You've been saying that
for how long now?
Two years, he's been gone.
Just let it go already.
There's a rumor
he can't even hear.
- Only one way to find out.
- Takeshi!
- I know that it's stupid.
I know that.
- [gasps]
- I don't care about Europe
or kicking ass
in the Chopin Competition.
All I want to do
is defeat Arima.
Wherever he plays, I play.
["Hikaru Nara" playing]
[singing in Japanese]
- [gagging, coughing]
[panting]
You're all right.
You got this, man.
Just play.
[audience murmuring]
[footsteps echoing]
- Good entrance.
Now don't
get ahead of yourself.
[applause]
[applause continues]
[applause ends]
[playing
"Etude Opus 10, Number 4"]
Yes. Nail that intro.
- Eh? Huh?
- Damn it.
["Etude Opus 10, Number 4"
playing]
- Huh?
Scoping out
the competition, huh?
She's got some guts.
EMI: You?
- Are you watching?
Do you hear me...
Arima?
TSUBAKI: It's the same piano.
So why does this
sound so different?
- Confronting the music
with sincerity.
Standing up to his fears
through sheer force of will.
An inner reservoir of strength
that belies his years.
This is Aiza's Chopin.
- I suppose
I should thank you, Arima.
Just by
your playing the piano,
by your mere existence,
you've spurred Takeshi
Aiza
to be the best he can be.
TAKESHI: You've been gone
for two years,
but I hung in there,
because I was certain
you'd return someday.
Have I caught up to you yet
or fallen further behind?
If I chase after you,
are you gonna vanish again?
Will you be
what I aspire to be?
Answer me.
Show me what you've got.
Come on.
Time to deliver, Arima.
It's now or never!
[audience cheering]
[sighs]
[cheering continues]
[chuckles]
- Amazing!
- Bravo!
- [scoffs]
I guess he's kinda cool.
- See what I mean?
- That was incredible.
- [girls yelling]
- Eh?
[girls clamoring]
Uh, what?
- They're Takeshi fangirls.
Nothing beats
having a good rival.
He's worth his weight in gold
to a boy like Takeshi.
Arima lights a fire under him
that my lessons
could never hope to.
EMI: It's your fault, you know?
- [gasps] Huh?
- Takeshi never would have
mastered the piano like he has
if it weren't for you.
- [sighs]
- Surpassing you
is all he cares about.
Every note is a battle cry.
- Do you feel that way, too?
- Don't make me laugh.
- [breathing heavily]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[sighs]
It's over.
- That was great.
- Well done.
- [sighs]
Oh, now my hands start shaking?
[footsteps pattering]
- EMI: Not bad.
- [gasps]
[grunts] Yeah, Arima!
Did you hear me?!
- Uh-huh.
You were great out there.
- [gasps]
- [sputters] Huh?
Really, that was nothing.
Nice of you to say it, though.
[laughing]
EMI: Sellout.
- Attention. We'll now take
a 15-minute intermission.
Judging will resume...
- He was really cool, wasn't he?
- at a quarter 'til.
- That guy killed it.
- No question.
Aiza owned that stage.
- He brings
a daunting level of focus.
- And no mistakes to speak of.
- You can tell he's
run that piece night and day.
- He doesn't look the type,
but he's really rather diligent.
- Well, more so than his
mentor,
Takayanagi. That's for sure.
- Oh. [laughs]
- TAKAYANAGI: Hmm?
- He's placed first in all
of his recent competitions.
It's clear he's been
on a real winning streak lately.
- That boy is going
to take the world by storm.
She, on the other hand...
doesn't seem to be
living up to her potential.
- [growls]
[growls]
Man, what a cutie!
- Yeah? Let me see.
- Huh? [shrieks]
Oh, crap.
- That's Igawa
you're looking at.
She is pretty popular.
- I knew I'd seen 'em somewhere.
When I used to cheer Kousei on,
it was always that boy,
that girl, and him.
The others would do well
one week or bomb the next,
but these guys were always
a lock for the top three,
and the first-place prize
went to Kousei every time.
- You'd think
you were his coach,
the way you crow about it.
Anyway, is this Emi chick good,
or what?
- Eh?
- 'Cause she's so hot,
I can't imagine her being bad
at it. You know what I mean?
I'm pretty good
at reading people,
and she's gonna be
the one to beat today.
You can quote me.
KAORI: Hotness isn't a factor.
TSUBAKI: Try telling him that.
- [sighs]
Actually I think Igawa's
been struggling a bit lately.
Honorable Mention
at the Kumagai.
Third place
at the Tanizaki Festival.
And the other day, she didn't
even make it past the prelims.
- Really? Sounds like
she's been off her game.
[Watari chuckling]
- I wonder what
might have happened
to knock her off her pedestal.
- Why, hello.
- Oh, Mr. Takayanagi.
- A pleasure to see you,
Ms. Ochiai.
By the way,
how go things with dear Emi?
- Here to gloat. Of course.
Aiza's performance was amazing,
all thanks
to your tutelage, I'm sure.
- Well,
that's kind of you to say.
I may have taught him
a thing or two.
[laughing]
- [groans]
- Honestly, though,
it's time to shift his focus
to the world stage.
There's nothing left for him
to prove on the domestic
level.
No one can touch him in Japan.
He showed you as much.
Takeshi is number one
with a bullet.
All that's left
is to dismantle Arima.
- [sighs]
Best of luck, then.
- Back on topic, though.
How's Igawa?
- As you know,
she can be very temperamental.
The least little thing
can throw off
the girl's equilibrium,
like the way a new pair of shoes
might pinch at her toes,
or someone might hum
too incessantly
near her backstage.
Even the weather
can break her focus.
[sighs]
It's been a real battle
these last two years
sparking her motivation
on the competition scene.
Her only worthy foe
was nowhere to be found.
All of that changes today.
- Wait a second.
"Nowhere to be found"?
[gasps]
"Her only worthy foe"?
- [gasps]
- So Takeshi
doesn't pass muster?
- In much the same way
Emi doesn't pass muster for him.
- [chuckles]
- Not that I know
what it's like
to have a good foe.
- [sputters]
Those could be mistaken
as fighting words, Ms. Ochiai.
- The mistake would be
you acting upon them,
Mr. Takayanagi.
We women can be
such combative creatures.
Do forgive me...
boy.
- [sighs]
[buzzer]
- Judging of the competitors
will now resume.
- Aiza's time at the top
ends today.
My Emi will dethrone him.
[footsteps echoing]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
- [grunts softly]
[groans] Goose bumps.
Am I nervous?
[chuckles]
Haven't felt like this
in a while.
Two years.
An eternity.
- Back when I
was five years old,
I attended a piano
recital
to support a friend of
mine.
Just as I was
nodding off from boredom...
- [footsteps echoing]
- he marched out onto the stage.
- [whimpers]
[gasping]
- The boy was so tightly wound.
It made me nervous.
- Arima showing his nerves?
[laughs]
- That was his first time.
Turns out he had never played
in front of a real,
live audience before.
- [chuckles]
- That long silence
before
his fingers touched the
keys
as he stilled all
the uncertainty in his heart.
The moment he pressed
that first gleaming key,
my destiny was made clear.
- I did it.
[gasps]
- [whimpering]
[crying]
- [sobbing]
- [gasping]
- [gasps]
- You started bawling
right there?
- Even now, I'm mortified.
- I'm sure that had to be
awkward for poor, little Arima.
- He looked pretty glum
as he walked off.
My heart wouldn't
stop pounding away,
and my eyes filled with tears.
My emotions poured out
in a flood.
His playing...
it touched my soul.
In that moment, I felt...
all the joy of music.
He was magical,
but he didn't play like that
for very long.
- He's like a machine.
- Nothing but
his mother's puppet.
- Slave to the sheet music.
- Good for competitions,
and that's it.
OCHIAI: Arima's mother, Saki,
she must have had
big plans for the boy.
And why not?
She put him in that competition
as a test,
and when he passed
with flying colors,
the dreams took root,
dreams she would never
get a chance to pursue.
And so she pushed Arima,
pushed him into sterile,
winning perfection.
- [metronome ticking]
- Play only what's on the page,
like a machine.
And it worked.
As an instructor,
I know that's what the judges
are grading them on.
But you're different,
aren't you?
You're strong, Emi.
TAKESHI: Yeah,
she's distant and prickly
and kind of bites
at human interaction,
but Emi really does
have a thing for you, Arima,
so yeah.
- For me?
- Really. No kidding.
Like she can't get you
out of her head.
- [gasps]
- Back in the day,
she'd always tell me,
"Takeshi, you don't know
anything about the real Arima."
- So beautiful.
- She's pretty.
- She takes my breath away,
her and that black piano.
Man, just look
at the two of 'em.
[playing
"Etude Opus 25, Number 11"]
- That's a lovely sound,
but it's not enough.
- [gasps]
- It's true
that Emi can be erratic.
Her emotions are a sea,
placid one moment,
then tempestuous the next.
And today I think those waves
are going to reach
new heights.
- Man, oh, man.
- The piano and I,
we're in cahoots.
We're such a team today.
Maybe it's because
I had that tasty scone
or because my new dress
looks good on me
or because my hair
is actually behaving.
Mystery solved.
Of course not.
It's none of that.
Don't lie to yourself, Emi.
You know
why today's going well.
After two long years away,
he came back.
He's gotten taller, of course,
and he looks
a little more grown-up,
but I knew him at a glance.
My excitement's
been building ever since.
He's backstage right now
watching me.
KOUSEI: Do you
feel that way, too?
EMI: Don't make me laugh.
The truth is I've been playing
the piano all these years
because I feel
nothing like you.
- I knew she had the technique,
but this is something else.
- Go, Emi.
That's it. Let it all out.
Fill the concert hall
with your emotions.
- A 14-year-old girl
has this audience practically
forgetting to breathe.
She's not even
in high school.
This is me
rejecting you, Arima.
You can beat me.
utterly trounce me,
but it isn't
going to change a thing.
Hitting keys like a robot
just to win is worthless.
I reject you with every note.
I want to hear a tempest.
- [gasps]
Red...
and then yellow.
Are these her emotions?
Red and yellow,
anger and...
Do you feel that way, too?
- Yes, of course.
You're the whole reason
I'm here, Kousei Arima.
Four minutes of my life,
four minutes
of him at the keys,
that's what made me a pianist.
Return to me.
Return to me the Kousei
that set me upon this
path.
Let it ring,
every note, every chord,
every measure.
Let it ring.
Let it ring. Let it ring.
KAORI: I see them,
red and yellow,
her anger and...
her loneliness.
Chopin's "Etude
Opus 25, Number 11,"
"Le vent d'hiver,"
"Winter Wind."
- [exhales]
[audience cheering]
- Super cute!
- Put a sock in it, Watari!
- I see.
Your pour your heart and soul
into the notes
just like I do, huh?
[cheering continues]
EMI: Let it ring.
Let it ring. Let it ring.
Let it ring.
["Kirameki" playing]
[singing in Japanese]