- Wanna kill yourself with me?
Come on.
I didn't mean it,
but honestly...
[COALAMODE.'S
"Nanairo Symphony"]
♪♪
[singing in Japanese]
- Are you going to forget?
- Hey, Kousei.
you feel sick or something?
- I'm fine.
- Well, you look pretty
wrecked.
I'm just saying.
How about we go pay Kaori
a visit later on?
I bet she'd love to see us
all together like that.
Let's do it.
It'll be fun.
- Yeah, good call!
- Maybe next time,
all right?
[dramatic music]
- You think he
and Kaori
got into a fight, maybe?
♪♪
- Who knows,
and so what if they did?
- Because they're friends.
- Yeah, they're friends,
but she's also the competition.
- We're not competing.
If he's all bummed out about
some music thing,
it's not like I can help
him out with it.
He's down in the dumps.
Taking him to see Kaori
seems like a no-brainer.
- Just make sure you're
not sabotaging yourself, okay?
You've been studying for that
high school entrance exam
like crazy.
You chose a school that's
way out of your league,
all because it's close
to that music prep campus
Kousei's been looking at.
- It's obvious.
- [grunts]
[sighs]
♪♪
- Well, it's just that Kousei's
so helpless on his own,
I have to go with him.
- You could just be honest
with him, you know.
It'd be a lot easier.
- The truth is,
I wish he'd go someplace local.
Thinking about it,
I get nervous,
and I get kinda mad at him.
- When he said to go
without him,
I felt so relieved,
and so guilty, too.
'Course, I don't want Kousei
to see me like that,
so I gotta keep up
my game face.
Maybe I'm just a horrible
person on the inside.
♪♪
I'm finding all
these sides of myself
I didn't know,
and once I've seen them,
I have to deal with them.
I guess that's just part
of being in love.
[smacking]
- [sighs]
I don't know where your head
is at, Kousei,
but it sure ain't here.
call it a day.
- [grunts]
- Yeah, you're right.
[door opens]
- Ah, I have to leave,
Ms. Seto!
I forgot there's something
I need to do!
- Uh, yeah.
Try to cheer him up,
would you?
- [grunts]
- Hey, wait up, Arima!
[breathing heavily]
You're way taller than me
but I was still able
to catch up
to you pretty easily.
You know why that is?
It's 'cause you're slouching!
How else could my tiny legs
catch up to you?
So he looks at me and says,
"When I play my oboe
at the festival,
know it's for you, Nagi."
He meant for it to sound cool.
Like I would be impressed
by that.
- Honestly, so that wouldn't
impress you even a tiny bit?
- Only if the guy's cute.
- [chuckles]
- [grunts]
- And I'm guessing he's not.
- I finally made you laugh!
- [grunts]
- [chuckles]
- Thanks for that, Nagi.
I hope I didn't worry you guys
too much.
- Who, me?
Worry about you?
That's ridiculous!
I was just telling
a dumb story!
Having a depressed enemy
is boring, that's all.
- This Arima guy
is unbelievable!
Everyone's freaking out
'cause he's got
the whole song memorized
and he acts like it's
no big deal.
He was like the sheriff
in some western,
or like some giant robot
with a heart of pure steel!
Like a hero,
you know?
[dramatic music]
Damn it!
- What do I say
that won't make it worse?
"Best of luck?
Maybe you'll finally
beat him?"
None of that changes anything.
I'm here because Takeshi needs
to beat you,
and if you're too depressed
to put up a good fight,
the win won't make
things better.
How selfish, right?
I'm an ugly phantom.
- You know what I think?
That oboe is going to be great.
- Huh?
You really think so?
- When you play for the sake
of another person,
it can make all the difference
in the world.
- Why do you play piano
in the first place?
Is it for yourself?
- It's like you
and that one friend of yours.
The one you really admire.
You're playing for him,
whether he knows it or not.
- When you've shared your art
with a room full of people,
when you've given them
a window into your soul,
and your hearts beat as one,
that's the moment when music
goes deeper than words.
♪♪
- What does that even mean?
If cliches are
the best you've got,
you might as well
save your breath.
[swing squeaking]
♪♪
- [grunts]
Revel.
- Welcome back!
- [grunts]
No, I don't want to hear
"Pavane for a Dead Princess!"
- Wanna kill yourself with me?
- Welcome back.
- Don't make me!
Don't make me think about it!
I wish that I couldn't
hear anything.
- What's up?
We're heading over
to the hospital
to go pay Kaori a visit.
Love to have you come with us.
- I don't think so.
- There's no need to hold back
because of us, man.
Come on.
- No, all right?
- What is with you today?
- [grunts]
- Seriously, why are you
giving her the cold shoulder?
After all that Kaori's
done for you,
the minute she gets sick,
you jet?
- [groans]
- [grunts]
You're being a dick!
Hey, man,
are you okay?
- Watari.
- [gasps]
- What am I supposed to do?
- Honestly,
I'm in pretty bad shape here.
- [gasps]
No, not again.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm making you
remember things
better left forgotten.
You'd be happier
if we had never met, huh?
- [crying]
I just stood there
like an idiot.
I didn't know what to do.
What am I supposed
to do?
[crying]
- Listen, Kousei.
This is just my opinion,
but I really think that
you should go see Kaori
no matter how tough it may be,
'cause if it was me
that she needed right now,
I would do anything.
She could say the word
and I'd drink toilet water.
Just chug it down.
You know what, though?
When it comes to Kaori,
I'm pretty sure that I'm not
the guy she needs right now.
Whenever she stops being
stubborn and wants help,
it isn't me.
It's you.
- Enter a competition.
Be my accompanist!
I want a canele.
You don't know how close
I am right now
to just losing heart!
- But when I see her, Watari,
what do I say?
- Anything.
In the moment,
you'll know what's right.
Sometimes we fellas
gotta wing it.
- It feels so impossible.
- Like I told you before,
I think that's up to the girl
to decide.
[dramatic music]
♪♪
- I kind of figured
that you'd never come back.
- [grunts]
Remember?
I promised you some caneles.
- [grunts]
Have you been practicing?
- Yeah.
- How's school?
- Same as always.
- Is everyone good?
- Fine, I guess.
- Those answers all suck!
I bet you don't even wanna
be here in the first place!
- Well, I do!
The truth is,
my answers all suck because
I don't know what to say.
- Then go back to how
your life was before.
All you have to do
is forget about me.
Just press the reset button
in your mind.
One tap and you're done.
- Why?
- I'll never forget.
I'll be gone
and you won't have to be sad.
No point remembering me.
I'm a violinist who can't hold
her own bow anymore.
I'm pretty useless.
- Why?
Why would you say such
a thing?
After all of the yelling
and drama,
after dragging me back onto
that stage,
the memories I've made
with you,
they're precious to me.
[grunts]
[angrily chewing]
- No, not the caneles!
- You just told me
to forget you,
so I guess they're mine now,
huh?
- That is a jerk move!
- Well guess
who bought it!
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
- Ooh!
- Not again.
- You're a piece of work.
You know that?
Fine, I'm out of here!
- Wait a sec!
[groans]
[laughing]
You're a weird guy.
You know that, Friend A?
- All of this,
I hate it.
It tears me up inside.
You've given me more
than I could ever repay.
But still,
isn't there anything
I can do for you?
- She could say the word
and I'd drink toilet water.
- It's the reason
I play piano,
because he inspired me.
I want him to know that.
- Look at what I drew!
[upbeat music]
- [gasps]
♪♪
- What?
You wanna play
at my school festival?
This came out of nowhere.
I don't get it.
What the heck is he thinking?
- Don't look at me.
- Please, Nagi!
- I accept.
- [gasps]
- No way!
But this is your time to shine!
- Wait, she agreed?
Now what do I do?
I didn't think this far ahead!
- You did this
to yourself, Kousei Arima.
I'm surprised you want to,
but I haven't picked out
a song yet
so this works out pretty well.
- That's a relief.
- [groans]
I gotta ask, though.
What made you wanna do this
in the first place?
[school bells chiming]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
- Greetings, my petite princess.
I was hoping we could perhaps
bond over "Der Rosenkavalier."
- I reserved a cozy booth
at the restaurant.
- Hey, Nagi,
you want a crepe
on the way home?
- Rain check!
- Hmm?
- Huh?
- Hot date?
- [humming]
- Try to give it
some more lilt.
It all comes down
to wrist control.
- [chomps]
- Maybe you should wait
for an extra beat at the top.
Speeding up the intro
might serve as a nice hook.
- [humming]
No way!
How many times did you run it?
It was great before,
but now...
- Hmm?
Aren't you hungry?
- No.
I'm just gonna eat later.
Dibs on the piano.
[door opens and closes]
- It feels like she's pushing
herself too hard.
[piano keys clunking]
- That isn't how it goes!
- I'm sorry!
- It's fine.
Just take a breath
and play it through.
- Focus, dummy, focus.
You've got this.
[dramatic music]
♪♪
- Good luck, Nagi!
We'll be there cheering
you on!
- You're the main draw
this year.
- They say Mr. Ibata
will be attending.
That means you have
to be perfect.
Pass muster with him
and you're on your way.
- I hear they're sending
out a reporter.
Nagi's gonna get
a whole article written
just about her.
♪♪
- [crying]
- Four days to go.
I'm looking forward to this.
- That's all that's left?
I only have four more days
to make this piece my own.
- We're all with you.
- Would they care
if she wasn't cute?
- They'll probably run her
photo in that magazine, too.
- She's gonna own us.
- Loli it up more,
princess.
- Your parents must be
so proud of you.
- Good luck!
- Nothing but a pretty face.
- This is torture,
and I have to endure it
four more days.
♪♪
- Mm?
Ah, hey, Nagi!
[door closes]
[sighs]
♪♪
- Help me, Mom.
I can't hear--
I can't hear the notes!
- Two years later
and here I am again,
watching a kid melt down
in front of me.
♪♪
What's up?
- I'm so afraid,
even though it's just
for school.
It's not a competition
or anything,
so why?
- Welcome to the club, then.
We're all afraid,
even me and Kousei.
Heck, I betcha even
Takeshi Aiza feels it.
For those couple of minutes
out on stage,
it feels like your whole
damn life's on the line.
Scary as hell.
Always will be.
- So how come you do it,
Ms. Seto?
Why do you still put
yourself through that?
- 'Cause once you're done,
you can't imagine life
without it.
All the pain and the fear
just melt away,
and you're left with
something beautiful.
Something you brought to life,
Nagi.
- When you've given them
a window into your soul,
and your hearts beat as one,
that's the moment when music
goes deeper than words.
- Maybe we're idiots,
all of us chasing
that magic moment,
willing to brave whatever peril
to taste that high.
It's a little
like being in love.
- It is magical, huh?
- Got you, you little booger!
Don't go hogging all
the bathroom!
Hold onto that leg
for dear life, Koharu!
I know why you wanna stay
in here forever, okay?
You're afraid to walk out
on that stage
because you practiced
your little heart out.
You gave yourself,
body and soul,
to the piano.
Now you're afraid that maybe
it wasn't enough.
Just know this.
If anyone gives you the least
bit of grief at the festival,
I'll kick their ass into space.
So puff out that tiny chest.
Remember, you're Kousei
Arima's apprentice!
- [gasps]
I'm not his apprentice!
I'm his mortal enemy!
- That's the spirit.
Once you've taken the stage,
you can duke it out.
♪♪
- Watari?
- Yeah?
- I need a favor.
- Sure thing.
- But you don't even know
what it is yet.
- Long as you're
the one asking,
it's cool.
[chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughing]
I can't believe how many
cute girls they have here!
This festival's
a ten out of ten!
It's perfect!
- Why do I feel like we should
have Watari on a leash?
- Hmm?
Cool, there's a sign.
Looks like it's
already started.
[quirky music]
♪♪
- They should have picked
a shorter song.
This is torture.
- Hey, at least their
outfits are cute.
Nagi's turn is coming up soon.
Am I right?
How'd her song turn out?
- Dunno.
I asked her about it
but she refused
to tell me anything.
- So she's out
of that hero worship phase.
[giggles]
And how does big brother feel
about that?
- No complaints here.
- Good job, Komugi.
- [sighs]
I think that our number
went pretty well overall.
Hold on.
Where's Nagi?
- [groans]
We're following that?
- Look at you lazy kids!
[crowd laughing]
- They're cracking up!
Our waltz is so gonna kill
the mood!
- All in one place!
Wait, does that make--
- I didn't sign up for this!
- [humming]
- [grunts]
- How are you holding up?
- I'm fine!
Cool as a cucumber!
But why wouldn't I be?
Am I right?
So how are you?
If you're nervous,
I'm not seeing it.
Why is he so calm?
- Between the cute mascot suits
and the knife-wielding demon
right before us, I--
[grunts]
That's right.
The day we met,
her hand was trembling, too.
- [gasps]
What do you think you're doing,
you pervert?
Let go of my hand!
- If you squeeze
your hand so hard,
your fingers are gonna lock up.
Now open it and just relax.
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
- Welcome to the club, then.
We're all afraid,
even me and Kousei.
- We're both here
because we have to be.
Are you afraid, too?
The same way I am?
- A friend of mine
told me something.
Play with sincerity.
Give the performance
of your life
with everything
that you've got.
- I'll try,
but I'm only 13 years old.
What if my life's not enough?
- Nagi, it's not
about the number.
For you and everyone
who's important to you,
those years are
a precious thing.
Believe in yourself
and in your music.
- [grunts]
- All right, number eight.
Time for you
to take the stage.
- Well, that's us.
- All right, you ready?
- Uh-huh!
[applause]
♪♪
[singing in Japanese]
[7!!'s "Orange"]
♪♪