[ Insects buzzing ]
[ "Nocturne in D-flat Major,
Opus 27, Number 2" playing ]
♪♪
Kousei: I thought if I came
to the music room,
you'd be there like always,
but you're nowhere to be found.
I don't know your phone number
or e-mail.
I guess...
I don't really know
anything about you.
Kousei, there you are!
[ Yelps ]
It's about Kaori.
She --
She collapsed again.
[ Panting ]
♪♪
[ Kousei panting ]
[ Gasps ]
Hey!
Good to see you!
I wanted to let you know
what's up,
but I was kind of
out of commission.
I just figured
you'd back out without me.
Sorry I flaked on you.
[ "Nanairo Symphony" playing ]
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Insects buzzing ]
Tsubaki:
So, what'd you get her?
Watari:
Cake from Yoshitomo.
Girls have a sweet tooth.
Kousei: Her family
runs a bakery, Einstein.
Oh. A for effort,
though, right?
Ta-da!
Welcome back.
Hope you're
in the mood to pig out.
That's for me?
[ Gasps ]
So how you feeling?
Full of vim and vigor.
They just want to run
a couple tests.
I bet you fainted
'cause you miss me so bad.
[ Giggles ]
"Paging Dr. Watari."
Kousei:
It's happened twice now.
Didn't they run tests
on you last time, too?
Well, yeah, but they
want to be thorough.
You know how doctors are.
I did hit my head.
They want to make sure
this performance of mine
doesn't get an encore.
What's the big deal with
those wandering eyes, Friend
A?!
Or is it Friend T&A?!
Just look at you
drooling over me!
I swear I'm not
drooling over you!
I swear that I am!
It really threw us
for a loop.
No-show at the gala,
and then you're in here.
You're thrown?
Think of what I went through.
All I did
was bonk my head a little.
[ Wails ]
Blood everywhere,
gushing out like a hose!
It was like
a horror movie!
Anyway, my parents
totally freaked out
and took me
straight to the hospital.
The end.
Ooh!
Is that a tart?
I call dibs.
I have always
gotten tired easily.
Guess I pushed myself
a little too hard lately.
Got to learn to chill out.
Mmm!
She can't even
chill out about dessert.
Brought you some books,
too!
Time to kiss
your boredom goodbye!
Huh?! These are all
from the library.
Did you even
check them out?
No, but too late
for that now.
Your heart was
in the right place,
but isn't this
overkill?
How you figure?
Think about it.
Kaori's not gonna be away from
school for that long, right?
Mm-hmm,
not long at all.
-You see? That's what...
-Kousei: When she said that,
why'd it feel like...
-...too many books.
...she's practiced that reply
a few times?
Watari: We got to go,
but I'll see you in my dreams.
Tsubaki:
Dumbass. Later!
Thanks, you guys!
No way I'm gonna get
through this pile.
[ Gasps ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Door opens ]
Hey, Kaori.
Yeah?
Did your friends
call it a day?
Yeah.
Back to it, then?
Guess so.
Go ahead and hook me up
to the I.V. drip again.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Tsubaki: Oh.
Kashiwagi: You get a text?
It's Saito.
He says we should go
to the festival later.
Sounds a lot
like a date, Tsubaki.
Haven't you broken up
with him yet?
Why would I do that?
Why not?
What do you mean?
It's not like
I don't like the guy.
Do you like him?
Well, duh.
I've had a crush
on him forever.
So what's with Arima?
[ Sighs ]
Kousei: Tsubaki?
Tsubaki.
He's -- Wow!
Bringing up Kousei
when we're talking about Saito?
[ Laughs ]
You're so random, ain't ya?
Kousei's just...
We've been joined at the hip
ever since we were kids.
He's not like
a guy to me.
I see him as
a little brother.
I'm not sure that you do.
[ Gasps ]
But you think
if you say it enough times,
you'll convince everyone,
including yourself.
You're too chicken
to face the facts,
'cause maybe it ruins
the safe thing
you've got going
right now.
[ Grunting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Growling ]
The egg
is my favorite.
I was saving it
for last.
He's like a little brother.
That's all!
Well, that sure
didn't do the trick.
That's all!
Arima was afraid, too,
but he took the plunge.
Do what you want,
chicken,
but you got to
cross that road someday.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪♪
Hey, a yukata.
It looks good on you.
You're cute.
I mean it.
[ Giggles ]
It's just the same old me
dressed up
for a change.
It's all about
the yukata.
He told me I'm cute.
Kousei would never
say that to me,
'cause
when he looks at me,
all he sees is the big sis
who bosses him around.
I'm sure of it.
I can tell.
Kaori: The festival's
tonight, isn't it?
Yeah.
At ease, soldier.
Have a seat.
I could, I guess,
but I think I'll stand.
What you think I'm gonna do,
put a tack on it?
I don't like hospitals
much.
You'll be okay, right?
Those tests'll
come back fine,
and you'll be back at school
any day now.
We'll hang out
in the music room like before,
just the two of us,
won't we?
Are you gonna --
Hey, guess what.
Watari was just here.
He brought me a snack.
Watari.
We talked for a bit,
mostly about
your one-man "Liebesleid."
You forgot to mention it,
you know.
Uh, yeah.
The accompanist playing
a duet all by himself!
What kind of a showoff
does that?!
I mean, it was a violin
concert,
but whatever, right?
Good job, Friend A. Way to
totally confuse the audience.
It's your fault I had to
in the first place!
What do you mean?
When I didn't show up,
I thought you would
just go home.
I was gonna,
but this boy
insulted you.
Like always,
the notes disappeared on me.
Just when all was lost,
I thought of my mom.
My memories of her,
they turned into notes
and filled the hall.
See?
[ Gasps ]
You're a musician,
no matter what,
aren't you,
Kousei Arima?
Yeah, I was right.
"Love's Sorrow,"
she chose it because of me.
Whenever I hear it,
my thoughts always drift
to my mother.
The scent of clothes
in the sun.
The sound of the piano
all around me.
A quiet lullaby.
The smell of antiseptic.
Echoing footsteps.
A linoleum floor,
well worn.
I can't forget them.
Welcome back.
Your "Love's Sorrow,"
I wish I could have heard it.
You're okay, right?
I wish I could have
played with you again.
Tell me you're okay,
that the tests
are for nothing.
Tell me that you're
coming back to school.
You are, right?
That's twice now.
Huh?
Just now...
you called me
by my name.
Kaori...
you're not going
to leave me, are you...
like my mother did?
Welcome to the Sumiya Baseball
Youth Sports boot camp!
I'm gonna make sluggers
out of every last one of you!
[ Boys clamoring ]
Just for that,
10 sets of wind sprints
along the water!
Now move it!
[ Boys groaning ]
But I don't play baseball,
Tsubaki. Can I go?
What do you press those piano
pedals with, huh?! Your feet!
Hey, they're not that hard
to press, I swear!
Check out
those tiny, little prints.
They're not tiny!
They just look that way,
'cause you're Bigfoot!
What did you call me?!
I'm gonna use these big feet
to kick your butt!
-[ Wails ]
-Come back here, you!
[ Yells ]
Hey, Kousei,
want to go to the park with me?
I wish I could,
but I got to get home
for my piano lesson.
Hmph. I just
wanted to show him
this mud ball
I've been working on.
It's as shiny
as a marble.
This here is
a fine-looking specimen.
I should go pro.
I know.
I'll make one for Kousei, too.
Hey, Kousei!
Want to play some catch?
Just learned
how to throw a sinker.
Kousei's working to be
a top-notch pianist.
He needs to focus.
He can't risk his hands
on catch.
Scrub, scrub.
Sorry.
Scrub, scrub. Scrub, scrub.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Girl: Did you hear?
Arima gets to skip class today,
because he's got to practice
for some competition.
Boy:
Aw, no fair!
Ready. And...
♪ O Vreneli,
where do you live? ♪
♪ I really want to know ♪
♪ In Switzerland beside a lake ♪
♪ The water all aglow ♪
Stupid music. I hate it.
♪ La, la la, la la ♪
Kaori: Are you
practicing enough?!
I bet you're slacking
without me there to watch you!
Yeah?! Guess again,
Miss Know-it-all!
I'm running Hanon and Czerny
every single day!
Don't be a lazy butt!
Practice Chopin, too!
When am I supposed
to sleep, huh?!
That's it! And Liszt!
I don't know what
you're yelling about,
but calm down!
[ Arguing continues ]
Way to leave us out
of the conversation.
Kousei: I'm not listening!
♪ La la la la la ♪
[ No audible dialogue ]
Kashiwagi:
Time for some backup.
I'd let it go.
If I could,
we wouldn't be having
this little chat.
Yeah, but girls
who aren't in love with me
aren't my problem.
[ Chuckles ]
You know you said that
out loud, right?
[ Sighs ]
If somebody calls her on it,
she's gonna get all defensive
and then sulk,
and then life's gonna get
super complicated around here
for everyone.
Whatever Kousei is to her,
we just got to leave it be.
He's right.
It'll be a mess.
But even if it is,
I want Tsubaki
to smile again.
She has to figure it out
for herself,
even if she gets scraped up
along the way.
Kousei's
a lot of things,
but her kid brother
isn't one of 'em.
Young Man: Hey, Watari, we're
about to start the scrimmage!
Coming!
Thanks for the juice.
Anytime.
Do it herself, huh?
Thing is, people don't figure
stuff out until it's too late.
-Ah, Arima.
-Sir?
You're the only holdout.
Everyone else in my class
has made up their mind.
Hmm?
Choice of high schools.
What else?
Oh, right.
Kousei:
And since that's the goal,
I thought I should become
a crazy pianist, right?
[ Sighs ] Think it over,
but let me know soon.
Of course.
High school.
The future.
I wonder,
who do I want to become?
Tsubaki:
He dropped it in the sand and
wouldn't stop crying about it.
So I gave him mine
just to shut him up.
[ Saito chuckles ]
And he's all,
"I wish it was milk-flavored."
Eh?
I, uh...
I'm sorry.
There I go.
It's cool. Arima sounds
like a real character.
What am I doing?!
Look, he's your
next-door neighbor.
You got a lot
of shared history.
Dude's like
your kid brother, right?
No, he is not!
[ Gasps ]
What do I look like to you,
Kousei's babysitter!?
Tsubaki: What am I?
I'm the girl next door.
I used to be bigger than him
back when he lost his mom,
and ever since,
I've wished for
the old Kousei to come back.
Kashiwagi:
What are you, an idiot?
Listen to your heart,
already.
That's what
it's there for.
Yeah, thanks for that.
I don't even know what you're
trying to tell me, okay?
When we talked
about Saito before,
you were all, "It's not
like I don't like the guy,"
but "not like I don't like"
and like
are a million light-years
from each other.
Wait a sec.
That was a lot of "like."
I think you lost me.
You need to be honest
with yourself,
and quick, or someone's
gonna get hurt, Tsubaki.
If you don't feel it,
say so.
Of course I do.
I've had a crush
on you forever.
Do you like him?
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Who do I like?
How do I know?
Like, really like.
Like...
really like.
Like, really like.
Like, really...
[ Panting ]
like.
Kousei?
[ Gasps ]
Are you okay?!
Sick?! Hurt?!
Did you get food poisoning?!
What have I said
about the five-second rule?!
Kashiwagi told me
you were in trouble,
so I ran here
as fast as I --
[ Waves crashing ]
Huh?!
[ Sighs ]
She got me good.
I never would have
guessed Kashiwagi
was the type
to go pranking people.
Maybe she's human
after all.
[ Laughs ] I guess it is
sort of out of character
coming from her,
isn't it?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Laugh it up.
I ran here like a lunatic
thinking you needed saving.
[ Sighs ] I'm sweating
like a stuck pig.
I want a Popsicle.
You in?
[ Door chime rings ]
Clerk: Thank you very much.
Mmm.
Milk-flavored
like always?
I like what I like.
Check out that moon.
[ Kousei humming
"Clair de lune" ]
♪♪
Tsubaki:
[ Humming "Clair de lune" ]
♪♪
What?
I love right next door,
and you have played it,
like, a million times.
Oh, come on.
I don't play it that much.
Tsubaki: We're joking around,
talking like we always do.
[ Kousei humming
"Clair de lune" ]
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
It's way bigger than mine,
not like they were
in the old days.
♪♪
Something's different
about you.
Different?
Oh, yeah?
It's weird.
When our eyes meet,
my heart gets all fluttery.
I guess there's just
something in the air.
No doubt about it.
When it comes to Kouseis,
I'm kind of an expert.
Your eyes are
way sparklier now,
like you're full of glitter
and it can't wait
to burst out!
Most of all,
when you're playing the piano,
I can feel it, a gentleness
and a need to be heard.
It's like you're shouting out
to the world, "I'm right here."
Everyone
who hears you play
knows what you're about,
Kousei, what's in you.
[ Gasps ]
You're a musician,
no matter what, aren't you?
[ "For You" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
Tsubaki...
Hmm?
I-I found a school
that'll let me do music.
Oh, cool.
I didn't know we had one.
We don't.
I'd have to move.
Hiroko told me
I'd only have to go
to regular class twice a week.
Huh?
That said,
my getting in is a long shot.
[ Gasps ]
I am kind of rusty.
Uh...
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Sobbing ]
Tsubaki: It's happening again.
Music is taking Kousei
away from me.
Go then, you big dummy.
Go wherever you want.
What do I care?
We've been neighbors forever.
I used to be bigger than him.
And who lost his mom too soon.
I'm bossy, but really I just
want him to smile again,
to smile at me.
Kousei's the boy I always
figured would be around.
He's the boy I want
by my side forever.
[ Crying ]
♪♪
Tsubaki.
[ Crying ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪
I-I didn't know.
Scrub, scrub. Scrub, scrub.
[ Giggles ]
Can't wait for you
to see 'em, Kousei.
[ Giggles ]
[ "Orange" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪