- I gotta ask, though.
What made you wanna do this
in the first place?
- I have a friend,
and she won't stop
moping around.
It isn't good for her.
I just wanna kick her
in the butt a little bit.
- In that moment,
that's when I felt like
something inside
of him might change.
[COALAMODE.'S
"Nanairo Symphony"]
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Here goes.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- There she is!
- [gasps]
- She's pretty cute, huh?
- [grumbles]
[gasps]
Arima?
- No way.
- Is that who I think it is?
♪ ♪
- It's Kousei Arima.
- With Aiza's sister?
- Aren't he and Aiza rivals?
- I thought he retired
years ago.
[applause]
♪ ♪
- Elohim, essaim.
Elohim, essaim.
Most humbly I implore you.
- [gasps]
What does that mean?
- Don't know.
Worth a try, right?
- [gasps, giggles]
- [chuckles]
[piano music playing]
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
Good.
It's going well so far.
♪ ♪
- Nagi.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
In no time at all,
she's gotten way better.
♪ ♪
- Nagi,
knock 'em dead!
♪ ♪
- My fingers were
so stiff before,
but now they're moving.
The parts are clear.
Arima and I each have a job
to do.
All of that practice
is paying off.
♪ ♪
- It's hard to keep my focus.
Every note I play,
I can hear it.
♪ ♪
They're in my way.
If you won't help,
then go!
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[all gasping]
Just now,
what happened?
- [gasps]
The sound,
it's different.
- Kousei?
- This came out of nowhere.
What the heck are you doing?
You're supposed
to be helping me,
not playing it
totally different
than every other time
we ran it!
You're a liar.
You're an idiot.
Or both.
I've never heard it
like this before.
The rhythm,
the images crowding
into my heart,
everything!
This is an Arima
I couldn't have imagined.
- The tempo is definitely
starting to pick up.
His base line is going
to drown out everything
If she's not careful.
- All right, Nagi.
Moment of truth.
You gonna let Kousei boss
you around like this?
Give him hell, kiddo.
♪ ♪
- So be it!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Nagi!
- She's keeping up!
- Unreal.
- Aiza's kid sister's
holding her own.
- He's not going easy on her,
and she's still matching him
note for note.
Was she always this good?
♪ ♪
- That a girl, Nagi.
You're the star
of that damn stage.
Make sure he knows it.
♪ ♪
- [giggling]
- Wait a sec.
in a waltz,
the melody shifts
to the bottom part.
- No, you don't!
If you think you're off
the hook,
you couldn't be more wrong!
I've got you in my clutches,
Arima!
Two months ago I'd be
sitting here in tears.
All that practice,
it's paying off.
Every moment I spend
at the piano led to this.
♪ ♪
- Arima's got a heart
of steel!
It's like he's a robot!
Nothing even touches the guy!
- You're wrong.
Arima's no robot,
and his heart isn't made
of steel.
It's fragile
like anyone else's.
I know.
His hands were warm
when they held mine.
Something in that moment
reminded me
of all the time
we've spent together.
♪ ♪
- What Arima's doing
is perfect.
He knows her talents
and her weak points.
He plays to both,
forcing her to adapt,
and under such adversity,
She's growing
like never before.
- That sweet potato
he brought me,
it was so good.
And those pork buns we bought
on the way home,
they were delicious.
- This is their waltz,
every note of it.
♪ ♪
Nagi: the only reason
I started up with the piano
was to try and get
my brother's attention,
not for the music.
Takeshi,
these last few weeks,
I've been peering into
the abyss.
just a little, but still.
I cried till I threw up.
I went without food or sleep
just to give it my all.
looking myself in the eye
day after day,
knowing I wasn't good enough,
it hurt so much.
I bet you felt the same way.
- Playing for the sake
of another person
makes all the difference
in the world.
- Maybe so,
but that's not what
I want for you.
- [gasps]
- Keep fighting every day
twice as hard.
Give it your all, brother!
Your all and then some!
You've never been one
to lose your way.
Take those stairs like
they're nothing at all.
Take them two or three
at a time.
Let me chase you again,
just like I did
in the old days.
Be my hero again!
♪ ♪
- Uh-huh.
I'm sure those two would
rather die than admit it,
but they share a lot more
in common than they don't.
Right, Kousei?
- I'm not like
the rest of you.
I don't wanna go pro.
I'm not ready to dedicate
my whole life to music,
but that doesn't mean
no one's listening.
There are people
I wanna play for.
People who mean everything
to me,
and so I wanna be here.
Is that selfish of me?
It's a good enough reason
for right this second,
isn't it?
- What am I doing
in the audience?
sitting up here in the dark,
watching Arima?
Watching as they dazzle
everyone within earshot.
Emi, Nagi,
when you play,
how come it moves people
like it does?
Even you!
- Almost done.
It's a weird feeling.
I'm so exhausted but I just
wanna play till I pass out.
I wonder if I played
my part right.
Did I face the music
with sincerity?
♪ ♪
Hey, Arima,
tell me.
Why do the sounds you make
echo so beautifully in my head
and my heart?
Even now I feel like
I'm gonna cry.
- [breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
- Well, wanna bow?
- Oh, yeah.
- Here it is,
after all the weeks
of suffering...
[applause]
After plumbing
the depths of your soul...
- Amazing!
- Bravo!
- Marry me!
- Yeah!
- Nagi!
- You're left
with something beautiful.
- That's the moment when music
goes deeper than words.
- [sniffling]
Hey Arima,
do you think it reached him?
- Yeah, it reached him.
No doubt.
[both cheering]
- What about you, Arima?
- Hmm?
- Were you able to kick
your friend in the butt?
- Mm-hmm.
Think so.
This was pretty unforgettable.
[chuckles]
Hmm?
- Huh?
- What the what?
- [giggles]
I'm not the phantom after all.
I'm Christine,
and I just debuted
at the opera house.
- Your move, Takeshi.
Whatcha gonna do?
All these years of putting you
on a pedestal,
and now she turns in
a performance
like that with Arima.
It might be time for big bro
to take a cue from her
and get over it.
- Give it a rest.
- She gave the performance
of her life.
Doesn't that say anything
to you?
- [grunts]
- Of course you could
just sit here.
- We did it!
Yay!
[sighs]
[cheers and applause]
- That duet was so incredible,
Nagi.
- Nagi!
- [whimpers]
[both speaking at once]
- Uh, you guys,
you okay?
It was amazing,
but not 'cause of me.
[chuckles]
- [grunts]
- savor this moment, teach.
- Hiroko?
- This is what it's all about,
you know?
- Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
- [chuckles]
Nothing like it,
watching someone spread
their wings.
- I get it.
I finally understand why you
put Nagi under my wing.
- Ms. Seto!
Did you like our duet?
- [grunts]
Honestly, ever since you guys
started coming over,
life has been a hell
of a lot more colorful.
- [grunts]
- [giggles]
- Hey, Arima!
- Uh, hold on.
You're that guy Takeda, right?
- It's Takeshi!
Ta-ke-shi!
- Stop poking me!
- Listen up!
If you lay one finger
on my kid sis,
you're going down!
- Your kid sis?
- Introduction time.
Meet my big brother Takeshi.
- Huh?
But you said your last name
was Aizato.
- That's silly.
Who flubs their own name
meeting Hiroko Seto?
I'm Nagi Aiza, see?
You remember that,
don't you?
- That's what I heard.
- I heard it.
- Hmm.
Well then, guess I'm
the only one who got it wrong.
- Thanks for being
so gullible.
- So, why the hell were you
playing a duet with her?
That's what I wanna know,
you sleaze ball!
- I asked if she minded me
teaming up with her!
- Teaming up with
my little sister?
You think I don't know exactly
what that means?
I'm onto you,
you four-eyed horn dog!
- Can I please go home now?
- Stop it, Takeshi.
You're being a butt.
- What the hell?
Are you defending
this cradle-robber?
How'd you even get mixed up
with Arima, anyway?
Tell me!
- I met him a couple
of months ago.
You wouldn't believe
all the stuff
he's taught me how to do.
- Taught you how to do?!
- Thanks to him I'm way more
experienced than I used to be.
- Experienced?!
[crying]
- Takeshi!
- [grunts]
- [whimpers]
- Watch your back, man,
'cause the eastern Japan piano
competition is coming.
I'm gonna kick your ass up
and down the stage
for everyone to see!
- [grunts]
- Takeshi.
[door opens]
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
- Bring it on, Arima.
I dare you.
Playing a duet with my sister.
You've got a lot of nerve.
♪ ♪
- There you have it.
Nothing but musical drama
through to the end of the year.
- A tenth of my feelings,
even just 100th,
did any of it get through
to him?
Was my music enough
to carry them?
[gasps]
- You really shined out there.
♪ ♪
- Thank you so much, Arima.
Thank you.
[crying]
- Uh, hey, Aiza!
all: Hmm?
- Miike?
What's this about?
The guy's never acknowledged
my existence before,
and now he just yells out
my name?
- Tell me something, Aiza.
How come you were playing
a duet with Kousei Arima
of all people?
Is Kousei, like, a personal
friend of yours or what?
- Did you just
call him Kousei?!
Bite your tongue!
How dare you call him by his
first name,
you little twerp?
That's Arima to you!
Mr. Arima!
- Mr.?
He's, like, two years
older than us.
Why would I call him that?
You don't mean to tell me that
you got his phone number,
right?
- In my cell and everything.
We even stopped
for some taiyaki
on the way home yesterday.
Just him and me all alone.
- Nagi has his phone number?
They ate taiyaki
just the two of them?
Why?
I can't believe you get
to be his friend!
That is so unfair!
[crying]
- What was that about?
- ♪ Twinkle, twinkle
little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
[laughing]
I keep messing up that part.
♪ Twinkle, twinkle
little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
♪ Up above the world so high ♪
♪ Like a diamond in the sky ♪
♪ Twinkle, twinkle li... ♪
Hey.
- Hey.
- Is this guy your boyfriend,
Kaori?
- Boyfriend?
- Hmm?
No, he's not my boyfriend.
What this guy here is,
is a jackass!
- A jackass?
- Jackass!
- Huh?
That's totally unfair!
- What word would you use?
[piano music playing]
You take a violinist
who can't even play
and make her listen
to this song?
I didn't miss it before,
but now...
[phone beeps]
- I can't kill myself with you.
- I figured as much.
- Think about it.
When we went shopping,
you led the way the whole time.
I just followed you with all
those bags of cute stuff.
You're always five steps ahead
of me,
and I'm always bringing up
the rear.
Every time I think of you,
you're slipping farther into
the distance.
Technically speaking,
if we died,
it wouldn't be together.
I'd be following you,
just like always.
I want another chance
to stand by your side.
[dramatic music]
So please,
play with me one more time.
♪ ♪
- But I--I can't
even hold the bow.
- You don't have
to be the princess.
You're a girl in middle school
who has a sweet tooth,
not some tragic heroine,
and I won't play Ravel.
Not ever again.
One more duet.
That's all I ask.
As a good friend once said,
"Do you think
you can just forget?"
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- You're cruel.
You know that, right?
- I wouldn't say cruel.
I'm more of a jackass.
- The air is chilly
and dry as the fallen leaves.
The laundered sheets dance
to the rhythm of the wind.
You really are cruel
to come here like this
and speak of dreams.
My dream came true,
and that was enough for me,
or so I thought,
but here you are,
watering my withered heart
with your smile.
- Hey!
Stop it!
Don't make her cry!
- That's why you're a jackass!
- No, no, no, no!
I'm not being mean!
I swear!
Please stop hitting me!
Help!
- [laughing]
Maybe I'm just greedy,
but I wanna dream again.
♪ ♪
Someday we'll waltz together.
We just might.
[singing in Japanese]
[7!!'s "Orange"]
♪ ♪