[swing creaking]
- CAT: So...
- [gasps]
-...how have you been, Kousei?
- [sighs]
- That competition
is right around the corner.
- Yeah.
- What's with the long face?
Come on. Don't worry about it.
The worst
they're gonna do to you
is point and laugh
if you fail.
It's better
than being abandoned.
- [sighs]
- Let's be honest here.
You're no Beethoven.
More to the point,
you're no Chopin.
- I know that.
- Really?
Then tell me...
who are you in there?
- [gasps]
- While you're at it,
tell me where you are.
All right...
are you ready
to go on your journey?
["Hikaru Nara" playing]
[singing in Japanese]
- [running footsteps]
- [students cheering]
- [grunts]
[boys gasp]
[girls scream]
- Victory or death, Watari!
- Cover him!
- Cut to his right!
- He's going for the shot.
- Get that ball in the net!
[students groan]
[whistle blows]
[whistle echoing]
- With the blow of a whistle,
Watari's season
came to an end.
[player sobbing]
- So Watari's team lost, too.
That sucks.
- Dude, it's okay.
We gave it our best shot, right?
Come on. Time for the handshake.
- Watari, hey!
- Thanks for cheering us on.
- You were awesome out there.
- Well, that was
my chance at stardom.
Guess it's up to you now,
piano man.
- FAN: Good job!
- Huh?
- [player sobbing]
- WATARI: Dude,
we'll beat 'em in high school.
PLAYER: Watari. [cries]
- You're everything
a team captain should be.
COACH: Good try, men.
- The guys were all
counting on me today,
and I blew it.
[gasps] Damn it.
Damn it! We should have won!
I'm never gonna
let my team down again.
[sobbing]
["Etude Opus 25, Number 5"
playing]
KOUSEI: For Watari and Tsubaki,
their days of playing
in junior high are over.
And as for my competition,
I can play the piece
by heart, but...
[fingers tapping]
- Cut it out!
- [gasps]
- I'm trying to teach here,
for goodness' sake.
- [humming melody]
[boys panting]
- Show me some hustle,
gentlemen.
- [panting]
Watari and Tsubaki both
flourished under pressure.
and so did you.
["Etude Opus 25,
Number 5" playing]
You commanded attention.
Do I...
Do I even get Chopin?
Or am I just
pawing at the keys?
I can play this song
to perfection,
but am I in it?
- [click]
- [music stops]
CAT: While you're at it,
tell me where you are.
- [grunts]
[groans]
- Arima!
KOUSEI: I don't know.
- Quick! Get some water!
- Somebody go tell the nurse.
KOUSEI: I don't know.
I don't know.
- [panting]
Friend A! Where is he?
- Hmm?
- Really? [groans]
[birds squawking]
What is wrong with you, huh,
skipping out on meals
until you keel over?
How did you think
that was gonna work?
- I've been totally
focused on Chopin.
It's not like I meant to.
But Tsubaki brought me
some egg sandwiches,
and I scarfed 'em all down,
like five.
- Whoa!
[sighs]
Oh.
[gasps] Look who's back!
[heart beats]
CAT: While you're at it,
tell me where you are.
- [gasps]
[gagging]
Hey, are you all right?
Let's get you
to that park over there.
- When I was little...
I had a black cat.
She'd steal my candy,
so I figured that I
should name her Chelsea,
just like the butterscotches.
I was horsing around
with Chelsea one day
like I always did.
I guess I overpet her.
She got me...
right across the hand.
- [gasps]
- Blood everywhere.
Took a while to stop,
even after we wrapped it up.
The next day, my mom
abandoned her somewhere.
[train cars rattling]
- I'm doing this for you.
- The scars Chelsea left me,
they remind me of my mom.
It's one of the few memories
that I have of her...
[footsteps echoing]
staring at her back
as she took Chelsea away
and I don't say a word.
All I had to do
was say, "Stop it,"
or, "Wait a minute."
Maybe she would have.
[train cars rattling]
Ever since...
I've been that little boy
stuck in her shadow.
- You like egg sandwiches.
And your favorite kind of milk
is Moo Moo brand.
It's good for washing down
all those sweets you eat.
Sports are not your forte.
Tsubaki's always been
like a sister to you,
and you're kinda jealous of
Watari's way with the ladies.
You see? You're not
in your mother's shadow at all.
You're just yourself.
And the best part is you
don't have to do anything.
Change all you want,
or don't change at all.
You're you, no matter what.
You weren't born in Poland,
and you don't have
some crazy mid-1800s haircut.
Guess that means
you're not Chopin after all.
Just play with sincerity.
Give the performance
of your life
with everything you've got.
- [sighs]
I don't know how, but...
you said what I needed to hear.
- [chuckles]
[train horn honks]
What do you mean,
you "don't know how"?!
It's 'cause I'm so smart,
you ingrate!
- Sincerity.
Eh?
[sighs]
- "When you're depressed,
it always helps to lean
your head on your arms...
because arms like
to feel useful like that."
- Who's that a quote from?
- All Charlie Brown.
Look at your hand,
at the spread of the fingers.
It's the hand of a pianist.
- Oh, wow. Feel that?
- [gasps]
- Your hand's about ready
to jump out of its skin.
- [stammers]
- More than ever, it wants
to get to a piano and play.
- [sighs]
I suffered and struggled...
but in the end,
the answer I arrived at
was so laughably simple.
CAT: So how have
you been, Kousei?
- Can't complain, I guess.
- Tomorrow's the big day, huh?
Any luck with that
hearing-the-notes thing?
- Mm-mmm.
- What will you do?
- It's hard to say.
But I met this girl, and...
she believes in music more
than anyone I've ever known...
believes with all of her heart.
That's why I'm gonna try
to believe in it, too.
- That isn't much of an answer.
- No kidding.
- I suppose you're
as ready as you can be.
Just know
she's going to be there.
- [sighs]
- You should try
and take it easy tonight.
Tomorrow's gonna be
a big day for you.
WATARI: Whoa!
TSUBAKI: They're doing
the contest in there.
WATARI: Dude, it's humongous.
- Well, gotta go.
TSUBAKI: Uh, Kousei.
- You're going the wrong way.
- Is he gonna be all right?
- [gasps]
- Huh?
KAORI: No, come back!
- Wait! What's up?
- [grunts]
- [wails]
What the heck?
- [panting] Look at this.
- What, the contestant list?
- Yeah. Check out
your entry number.
As in Kochel number 265,
as in Mozart's
"Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star."
It means that you're gonna
shine like a star up there.
- [chuckles]
[laughs]
A star in the daylight.
TAKESHI: Hey. Is that...
EMI: Yeah.
KOUSEI: Time to face my past.
[gasps]
My competition begins...
right now.
- All right!
- Lookit! There's my name!
- Did your boy
place in the finals?
- Of course he didn't.
Look at the competition.
With them here,
he may as well have stayed home.
Emi Igawa and Takeshi Aiza,
those two are basically
in a league of their own.
You can tell
they practice night and day,
and this was the payoff.
I kind of feel bad for them.
In the end,
neither one can touch Arima.
WOMAN: Second and third,
just like clockwork.
- Arima really pisses me off,
you know.
- Mad because you lost again?
- Hey, I'm just lulling him
into
a false sense of superiority.
I hate that guy.
He's such a jerk.
He left without looking
at the results,
like he knew he won.
Would it kill him
to celebrate a little bit?!
That pisses me off even more!
- Far as I can tell,
he just doesn't care,
not about other people
and not about us...
maybe not himself, either.
- You sure are chill about it.
- Chill?
The truth is I've never
been more humiliated.
- Hot!
- So what if Arima
doesn't care about us?
That's all the more reason
to command his attention.
I'll make him care...
someday, I swear.
I'm going to destroy you.
TAKESHI: He's taller
than he used to be.
Same dumb glasses,
and he's ignoring us
just like he used to.
Bastard.
Hey, been a while.
- Huh?
- Right, Arima?
- I, uh...
[stammers]
What was your name again?
[audience murmuring]
TSUBAKI: Not a lot
of people here, huh?
KAORI: Au contraire, Tsubaki.
This is a pretty good crowd
for prelims.
Could be because of Arima.
- Weird moment in the bathroom.
These two guys
kept going on about Kousei.
He's a big deal here, isn't he?
- Mm-hmm.
- What are you so smug about?
You're not his manager.
- [groans]
- Listen, though.
They weren't exactly
talking him up.
- We already know how
he's gonna play the song.
- Nothing but the notes,
like he's a robot or something,
just like Mommy taught him.
- The stuff they were saying,
it's like they hated him.
- It's a difficult thing,
playing a song
exactly as it was written.
It's nothing short
of incredible.
In a competition,
that's the only thing
they can judge you on,
and he's such a technician,
that plays to his strengths.
He'd win so easily.
It didn't sit well with people,
especially people our age
who want emotion in their music.
And of course...
there was
a fair amount of jealousy.
[sighs]
When you think about it,
he was unstoppable
at events like this.
- Yeah. For a while there,
he was doing a bunch of
'em.
Back when they hospitalized
his mom for the last time.
- Kousei runs
like a digital watch,
precisely, but no soul,
no resonance.
The Human Metronome,
the concrete boy,
his mother's puppet,
slave to the score--
Kousei's been called
all of that, if not worse.
- Who's been talking trash
about my friend?! I'll kick--
- Yeah! You messed
with the wrong pianist!
- Shush! Shush!
- Damn it!
He walks in here
two years later,
- and that little jerk...
- That's enough, Takeshi.
- has forgotten all about us.
- Calm down, already.
Your call time is coming up.
Temper tantrums
aren't going to help any.
Go and get changed.
The truth of it is
Arima didn't forget about us.
He never knew us.
Two years have passed,
but he's the same.
I don't like him.
Getting special treatment
just because his mom
studied with someone famous.
All the talent in the world,
and he refuses
to play anything with heart!
- [Takeshi growling]
- [Emi wails]
[Takeshi screams]
[buzzer]
- Attention.
The judging will now commence.
[applause]
TAKESHI: I've been
chasing this fool
ever since I was
in the third grade.
"Next time, man.
Next time for sure, yeah."
And just when I thought
I could beat him
after all those years of work,
he faded away like a mirage.
He was like the dove
in a magic trick,
gone just like that.
'Til right now,
when he waltzes in
like he never left.
- You've been waiting.
The both of us have.
- At last...
the competition begins.
[playing
"The Well-Tempered Clavier"]
- [groans] Judging these things
is such a chore.
- [light snoring]
- What the heck?
How are you already asleep?
- Watari, wake up.
[playing "Piano Sonata
in A minor D.845"]
["Piano Sonata in A minor
D.845" continues]
[no audible dialogue]
- Number three, Yuko Kawanaka,
you're up next, okay?
[water running]
- [gagging, coughing]
[panting]
You're all right.
You got this, man.
Just play.
[grunts]
- Weird.
- [heart beating]
It's never felt like this.
Is it because I've been gone?
My heart's going
a mile a minute,
slamming against my ribs,
like a broken seesaw.
- Oh, no.
- It's over.
- Why isn't he playing?
- Did he forget how to play?
- That's one less competitor.
- He self-destructed.
- I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared.
- Number four.
- [gasps]
- Takeshi Aiza,
you're next on deck.
- [sighs]
- I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
[footsteps echoing]
[door closes]
KAORI: I'm gonna
tell you a little secret.
Going onstage to play,
it scares all of us.
'Cause maybe you mess up.
Maybe the audience hates you.
Doesn't matter.
You walk out there
like you're ten feet tall.
[audience murmuring]
- Hey, Kaori,
did the mood just change?
- How could it not?
The guy who's about to play
is last year's champion,
Takeshi Aiza.
- Finally.
Now we're gonna hear
the real deal,
Chopin's
"Etude Opus 10, Number 4."
[applause]
- Good entrance.
Now don't
get ahead of yourself.
- Listen, I'm not
going to Germany.
I want to enter
the Maihou Competition.
- [gasps]
But they invited you over.
This is a golden opportunity
to get overseas exposure
before the Chopin contest.
You won the Maihou last year.
There's no reason
for you to do this.
- There is a reason, okay?
- [gasps]
["Kirameki" playing]
[singing in Japanese]