[insects buzzing]
[chalk scraping]
- This time, X equals four.
Once we pop that
into the formula,
finding Y
is pretty straightforward.
- [violin playing]
- You can derive
those coordinates up top
and plot those points
on your graph.
[piano and violin
playing "Love's Sorrow"]
♪♪
- [growls]
- [roars]
- [wails]
[sputters]
- You need to focus, mister!
- [groans]
I played it note for note.
- Yeah, like a robot
who isn't putting
any of his heart into it!
- Listen, does this have to be
our piece for the gala concert?
- Oh, man, not this again.
- All I'm saying is that we
should do something flashy,
give 'em more of a show.
- Flashy? Meh!
I happen to like our song.
Don't be such a worrywart.
Come on.
This duet is gonna
knock their socks off.
[grunts]
I know you won't wanna play it,
but I don't know why.
Something about it
spoke to me,
like choosing it was fate.
"Love's Joy,"
Friedrich Kreisler.
And here, "Love's Sorrow."
["Nanairo Symphony" playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪♪
- "Love's Sorrow,"
Kreisler's companion piece
to his earlier work for violin,
"Love's Joy."
A bit later, Rachmaninoff
did his own arrangement,
but for the piano.
That's kinda weird.
I don't remember that
being there.
[playing "Love's Sorrow"]
SAKI: Asleep under
the piano again.
You're going to catch a cold.
- [sighing]
- Look how big you're getting.
Dear Kousei.
[distorted notes playing]
This is your punishment.
The piano
isn't responding to you.
- I don't care anymore.
Now I just wish you were dead!
I can't hear!
Help me! Mom!
KAORI: I know
you don't want to play it,
but I don't know why.
- It's simple, really.
I can't hear this song
without thinking of my Mom.
[gasps]
[Koharu laughs]
[overlapping chatter]
[drum and flute playing]
- [Koharu laughs]
- Hiroko,
shouldn't I be running
the piece right now?
- All work and no play
makes Jack a dull boy.
A little fun
ain't gonna kill you.
- I wanna get cotton candy!
- Try not to barf it all up,
okay?! [sighs]
- [chuckles]
- Rachmaninoff's arrangement
of "Love's Sorrow," huh?
Your Mom used to play that
all the time back in school.
- And later on, too,
as my lullaby.
I think maybe...
maybe it comes
with too much baggage.
With every measure,
the old pain closes in on me.
That day in the lobby,
my Mom, she must have
hated me, right?
- She was sick and angry,
but she was your Mom, Kousei.
Think about it.
When you stood up for yourself,
you grew as a performer
and a person alike.
♪♪
[child crying]
- Huh? Eh?
- Ahh. Never scare Mommy
like that again, okay?
- Ohh.
- But it does break your heart
a little bit, you know,
watching your kid
get smaller in the distance.
- She's my Mom...
and I've tried so hard
to forget about her.
Do you think she'll
ever forgive me for that?
Is it all right
that I'm playing the piano
even though she's gone?
- It's better than all right.
If you get hung up,
just pour your heart into it.
That's what your Mom would do.
- She would.
- Worrying won't help you
prep that piece.
If you want it, you're gonna
have to work for it, Kousei.
So play.
We're pianists, you know.
It's kind of our shtick.
- [gasps]
- Want a candy apple?
- Uh...
- I got it for you.
You don't want it?
- Yeah, I'm sure they're great!
I've just never had one before!
No, no, no, no, no! Don't cry!
I'll eat it!
I'll eat it right now, okay?
See? See? I'm holding it.
HIROKO: Maybe I'm being
too tough on him.
- Eat it.
- But he's got to play,
not only to grow
as a pianist, but also...
KOUSEI: This is really good.
- ...so he can say goodbye.
[Kaori sighs] I can't believe
you're getting me home so late.
- I wanted to call it a night
before, but no.
- We needed that time
to practice.
- [groans] You're right
about it being late, though.
I wonder if your parents
are gonna freak out.
- Would you look at that
up in the sky!
- Focus!
- The stars are so beautiful.
It's like they're
speaking right to us.
- [gasps]
[chuckles]
♪ Twinkle, twinkle ♪
- ♪ Little star ♪
- Huh?
- ♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
BOTH: ♪ Up above
the world so high ♪
♪ Like a diamond in the sky ♪
♪ Twinkle, twinkle,
little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
- It's a pastry shop?
- [entry bell rings]
- I'm home!
Ooh, just wait here for a sec.
- It's fine.
I should probably get going.
- [gasps]
- How dare you
keep my precious daughter
out so late?!
- [whimpers] I'm sorry.
- [roars]
- I'm sorry.
- [growls]
Uh, Arima?
Oh.
- Huh?
- Look who it is, dear.
- Hey, come in! Take a load off!
- [shrieks]
- Eat your fill.
I know how ravenous
you kids get.
- [chuckles] Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
- Oh, what about
the sample items?
- Mm-hmm.
- Please, that's okay.
This is more than enough!
- They're big fans of yours,
so good luck stopping 'em.
Back when I was little,
they went to hear you play
a lot.
- You're in big trouble,
young man!
- [gasps]
- Cutting your performances
short like that.
Nothing good ever came
from throwing in the towel.
- Mm-hmm. It's like baking
a great spongecake
only to ruin it with too much
frosting in the very last step.
- Mm-hmm.
- Sorry about that.
- That said,
I respect a young man
with the courage
to do his own thing.
- Never let too much frosting
scare you away,
not in baking and not in life.
- I'll keep that in mind.
YOSHIYUKI: Hey!
Want to see some pictures
of Kaori from back
in grade school?!
RYOUKO: Oh, and
the kindergarten pictures!
KAORI: Why do you hate me?!
YOSHIYUKI: In case
you get hungry later.
- Thank you both very much.
I really didn't mean to intrude.
- We'll be at the concert
cheering for the two of you.
- Knock 'em dead.
- Well, then,
I'd better do my best.
- Okay, guys, say good night.
- So that was Kousei Arima.
Seems like a nice kid.
Wouldn't you agree?
- Yeah.
- Why?! Why'd they haul out
pictures of me as a newborn?!
And I was naked!
You saw me naked!
How am I going to live?!
- At least your parents
seem pretty cool.
- Sorry they pushed
all that food on you.
My Mom's got
a soft spot for strays.
- I'm a dog now?
- Hold on.
- [grunts]
Okay.
- Hey, did you get any taller?
- Taller? Not that I know of.
- Maybe it's 'cause you're
not always looking down
at the ground anymore.
Anyway, it sure has been hot.
What's up with that?
KOUSEI: Meaningless small talk.
Familiar scenery.
KAORI: And the humidity.
Ugh! That's the worst part.
Even at night, it's muggy.
KOUSEI: Nothing that stands out
in one's mind. Still...
- But, you know,
I guess summer is worth it
for all the fireworks.
- ...that night...
- [humming "Twinkle,
Twinkle, Little Star"]
[laughs]
KOUSEI: I'll remember it always.
[piano and violin
playing "Love's Sorrow"]
- Ugh! What is your problem?!
I told you to make that part
way more legato!
- If I change the dynamics,
the violin gets buried!
Did you think of that, genius?!
- Gotta love summer.
- KOUSEI: You're such a tyrant!
- You bought me
a shaved ice, right?
- Yeah. What do you think
I been eating here?
- [shrieks]
- It's summer, you dumb-ass!
That was my shaved ice,
you monster.
I'm sick of summer school.
I'm just done.
I wanna goof off
and go to a festival...
- Gotta love summer.
- ...watch some fireworks,
you know?
- Yes!
Then you shall have them!
- Hmm?
[Tsubaki laughs]
Now this is summer.
- They're so pretty.
- I hope we don't get caught
sneaking into the pool area
after dark like this.
- Who's gonna find us?
- Yeah, the teachers are all
long gone for the day.
- And refilling the bucket's
gonna be a cinch out here.
- You weren't thinking of
lighting those rockets, right?
- Uh...
- Huh.
[giggles]
- Whoa. She can laugh?
- Aw, man.
This just makes me
dread class even more.
- Hey, you did it to yourself.
- Huh?
- You wouldn't have to go
if you weren't such a moron.
- [groans] Shut up!
You're no genius, either!
- So what are the two of you
gonna do?
- Hmm?
- Huh?
- For high school.
You're not in class
over the break.
Does that mean you guys
are on the music school track?
- Honestly...
I haven't really given
my future any thought.
- [sputters] Uh...
- What I do know
is that me and Friend A
are gonna rock that gala!
The starring role
belongs to us!
Working together,
there's nothing we can't do!
- Attagirl!
That's the spirit!
- [Watari laughs]
- KAORI: Ooh. [laughs]
[both laugh]
- Sparkler party!
- Whoo-hoo! [laughing]
- Ooh! [laughs]
[both laughing]
KOUSEI: Yeah.
Those two look great together.
- KAORI: Careful!
- TSUBAKI: Hmm?
- You're gonna
get sparks on me!
- [growls]
What are you staring at?!
- Huh?! Nothing!
- Hah!
- [gasps]
- [sighs]
[girls squeal]
- It's so dark at the bottom.
I can't hear anything.
It feels like...
[memory] Help me.
Please help me.
I can't hear anything.
It's dark. It's dark.
HIROKO: The fact that you
can't hear your own notes,
it just means
you're not limited
to whatever your ears
are picking up.
KOUSEI: Limited to?
What else is there?
- The imagery you carry within.
The sound rising up
from the depths of your soul.
The silence you bring
to the table
drowns out everything else,
but your feelings
and memories
and all the sounds
that go with them,
haven't you ever
been able to feel them
soaking into
those muted notes you play?
Don't think of it
as a handicap.
Losing your notes,
it might be a gift.
- A gift?
- Cover your ears,
and forget about
what's on the page.
For now, it's enough
that you play what you feel.
I know you've got the chops
to pull that off, at least.
Tracing the sounds within you,
hearing your own
inner landscape,
maybe that's something your Mom
helped prep you for, Kousei.
KAORI: Did you get any taller?
Maybe it's 'cause you're
not always looking down
at the ground anymore.
Now I see you looking up.
[water flowing]
♪♪
[piano playing "Love's Sorrow"]
[humming melody]
♪♪
[humming stops]
[music continues]
- TSUBAKI: Are you all right?!
- WATARI: Kousei!
- Kousei!
- [gasps]
- [groans] Ow. Guh!
- So he's okay?
- Maybe not his head.
- Kousei, you idiot.
- [groans]
- How could you?
- Eh?
- Were you really
gonna go off and drown
in the shallow of a pool?
Everybody would blame me!
- What the hell kind of guy
head-butts you
- after you save his life?
- Kousei.
- [Tsubaki sobbing]
- Eh?
- Huh?
KOUSEI: It's just a pool,
and the moon is out tonight.
But maybe the light
can reach me
at the bottom of my dark ocean
the same way it reached me now.
[insects buzzing]
- Miyazono is playing,
too, right?
- Yeah, with that boy
who stopped in the middle.
They're taking a chance
on that pair.
- I don't know why, but I think
she's gonna pull it off today.
She's something special.
- Nah, she's gonna
drop the ball.
- She's the whole reason
I came to this thing.
[Miike scoffs]
- [laughing]
All right!
I'm totally anonymous!
- Oh, Emi.
- [yelps]
[groans]
- We should go get seated.
- What are you even
doing here, Ms. Ochiai?
I mean, uh, random lady?
- This random lady is the one
who told you Arima
was playing today.
- [gasps]
I don't even remember that.
My coming to this concert
has nothing to do with him.
I'm just here to enjoy
some violin music, honest.
- I grabbed you a program
at the door.
- Uh...
- Come on now.
It should be starting up soon.
- Know-it-all.
[playing "Zigeunerweisen"]
- No judging to be done today.
I can just sit back and enjoy.
- With a lineup this talented,
we're in for quite a treat.
Now then, it's almost time
for my favorite of the bunch.
- Is she trying
to give me a heart attack?!
She's pulling a no-show!
Like Michelangeli
or Pogorelich?!
Yeah, they were pianists,
and she's...
- They've already
gotten started in there.
- No sign of Kaori yet?
- I can't believe she's...
- If this chick
doesn't show up,
like, now,
we are totally screwed.
- I've been calling
her cell phone nonstop,
but it keeps sending me
over to voicemail.
[buzzing]
[buzzes echoing]
[insects buzzing]
- What do I do now?
This is a nightmare.
- Let's go backstage
and get you all set, yeah?
That way, you're ready to roll
whenever she gets here.
And as for you, keep calling
until somebody answers it.
- You got it, sister!
- Don't let me down.
- Aye, aye!
TSUBAKI: Best of luck!
[sighs]
- So what's the plan?
- I'll ask 'em
if you can take a slot
later on in the concert.
I mean, it's not
a competition today,
so they just
might let it pass.
So long as someone
is willing to trade with you,
we can wait on your partner
'til the last second.
- Kaori.
- If that doesn't pan out,
we're dead in the water.
- You're right. No other choice.
Where are you?
KAORI: It's your call.
I happen to like our song!
- I mean, weren't you
looking forward to this?
I should have never
let her get my hopes up.
[applause]
- It's almost
Kaori Miyazono's turn.
- I wonder what she's gonna do
this time around.
- I haven't been
this excited at a concert
in who know how long.
- You can't just ask me to--
- I'm begging you!
She's gonna roll in here
any minute now! I promise!
- Be that as it may,
I don't have the authority
- to make changes to the--
- What's this all about?
STAFF: Oh. Miike.
- I've heard that name before.
Yeah, he's the last kid
in their age group, isn't he?
- Of course. As winner
of the competition,
- he earned that slot--
- Awesome!
So, Miike, need a favor.
Any chance you'd let my pair
play after you today?
Our violinist is running late.
You know how it is.
- Who are you waiting on?
- Her name is Kaori Miyazono,
and I'm sure she'll be here
any minute now.
You'd be doing us
a real solid.
GIRL: Miyazono is playing,
too, right?
WOMAN: She's something special.
- No way.
[sighs] I won,
so I get to go last.
That's my moment to shine.
- Right, you are.
Sorry that I asked.
- That is the best time to play.
I don't blame him.
- I hope you understand.
I had to at least
give it a shot.
Okay. Guess we're
canceling after all.
- [Miike sighs]
- KOUSEI: Yeah.
- Well, it's her own fault.
If she really wanted to play,
she wouldn't be late.
I guess she's as undisciplined
in her real life
as she is up onstage
showing off.
The crowd kinda liked her,
and now she thinks
she can breeze in
whenever she feels like.
- Point made. That's enough.
- She's not even a musician.
A musician plays
what the composer wrote down.
When she plays, it's a disaster.
It's just a bunch of noise.
- Who the hell do you think
you are, you smug little brat?!
- No, let him be.
- Uh...
- Sorry to have bothered you
on your big day.
- That was wrong of us.
- Don't you bow to him.
He's knocking your partner down.
You need to stick up for her!
- You keep your spot.
You'll be the last
middle schooler
they hear today,
just like you wanted.
But know this.
KAORI: The starring role...
- Today, the starring role
belongs to us.
- The promoters' choice
for the junior high division,
Ms. Kaori Miyazono.
- All right.
- Finally, it's Miyazono.
- Wait. So she got here?
[crowd murmuring]
- Huh?
- Isn't he the accompanist?
- Yeah, but where's the violin?
- Arima's playing alone?
- This is blasphemous!
TSUBAKI: Kousei.
- ["Orange" playing]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪♪