[ Humming "Love's Sorrow" ]
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
Oh, that really hurt.
[ Sighs ]
My foot.
Huh?
I...
[ Drop echoes ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Siren wailing ]
[ Drop echoes ]
[ Humming "Love's Sorrow" ]
[ "Nanairo Symphony" playing ]
♪♪
[ Singing in Japanese ]
[ Playing
"Piano Sonata Number 8" ]
♪♪
Done, Ms. Seto.
Well, Teach, have at it.
I'm ready
for your feedback, sir.
No pulling any punches.
Hmph!
The pianissimo part sounded like
you were marching off to war,
and your rests
were just sloppy.
You wrinkled your brow
from start to finish,
and your posture's abysmal,
and quit gritting your teeth
like you're in pain.
Your left hand lags a bit
on the rhythm, too.
My hands are small,
so my fingers
can't reach as far across.
Move your wrists a bit,
and you'll be fine.
Play the first beat
with your little finger,
and then use that momentum to
take your wrist over like this.
Then just move it
to where you can play the note.
How about changing up
your pedal work?
Might do the trick,
right?
That isn't going
to help me win.
Honoring the score
is all that matters!
The score
is perfection,
and we are lowly servants
of that perfection!
Well, that was abrupt.
You can say that again.
Playing a song any other way
than how it's written down
is just the refuge
of a lesser musician.
[ Sighs ]
Kaori:
Just play with sincerity.
Give the performance
of your life
with everything you've got.
The score's not
some perfect thing.
It's there to interpret,
an emotional roadmap
left by those
who have come before us.
And I...
I'm just now learning
how to read them.
[ Gasps ] What a cliché.
[ Shrieks ]
Spouting sentimental drivel
like that.
No wonder you burned out
by my age.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪♪
Kousei: I have a bit of time
before the lesson.
Kaori: I realized
I hadn't heard
your dumb voice
for a while.
♪♪
Oh, that's right.
I should get her some sweets.
Like those canelés you wanted.
You always pop up
out of nowhere.
I'm not ready,
but here you are.
Hey, it's you.
Who are you again?
Wait! Amnesia?!
Is it 'cause
she hit her head?!
[ Distorted ]
Sorry to forget you,
but I haven't
seen your face lately.
If only
you'd come to visit,
maybe we could have
avoided this.
Actually,
I was on my --
You didn't happen
to see Watari, did you?
I'm here to surprise him
when he passes by.
Watari? Uh...
he's still at school,
I think.
I'll go check.
[ Gasps ]
Never let it be said
that I am not merciful.
Even though you abandoned me
to my fate,
I'm gonna give you
a shot to make things right.
I'll let you be
Watari's stand-in again.
Hmph!
It worked out before.
[ Grunts ]
[ Distorted ] And I bet
you can carry a lot.
[ Shoppers squealing ]
Kaori:
These prices are amazing!
Take your grubby mitts
off of that!
You're making those sundresses
all wrinkled! I'll destroy you!
[ Shrieks ]
I, uh...
I got a lesson to --
[ Gasps ] This tie-wearing
rabbit is adorable!
Look at
this cute stationery!
No!
Just send an e-mail!
Come to me, lost kid!
Not a problem!
Woman on PA: Lost child
at the front counter.
Woman: There you are!
[ Gasps ]
Mommy!
Oh, you scared me.
[ Sighs ]
[ Laughs ]
There's nothing
I enjoy in life more
than lending a helping hand.
Hmph.
So grab some of this.
The girl's mom,
she was crying.
Yeah. I bet she's been
worried sick about her.
No kidding.
But I guess we all put our folks
through the wringer somehow.
Hey, did you see?
When I held her hand,
she squeezed it really tightly.
What a cutie.
It's like she was telling me
not to let her go.
Maybe she thought she'd be
all alone in the world
if I let go of her.
Uh...
Oh, hold on.
Are you thirsty?
Oh, yeah.
I meant
to take it back before.
[ Both stammer ]
Let me get that.
Uniform skirt?
So you came to school today.
She must be feeling better.
See? She's fine.
Wait a sec.
Where's your school bag?
[ Gasps ]
Uh,
let's go find it.
[ Loud piano chord bangs ]
He's late!
Stop hitting the keys.
Kousei
ain't gonna show up.
What?!
Yeah. He texted me.
You tell me this now?!
And you're okay with this,
Ms. Seto?
He's being
irresponsible.
He'll get his.
I want to know why you're always
so eager to sell him out.
Huh? No!
I wasn't
selling him out.
I just appreciate
our time here so much.
Look, kid, I don't know
what game you're running...
[ Gasps ]
...but if you ever
do anything
to try
and dick over Kousei,
they're not gonna
find your body.
Well...
I guess you must care
for Kousei quite a lot, huh?
I'm kind of
his backup mom.
How come...
How come you're even
bothering with me as a
student?
Because I thought it might
give something to Kousei.
Something more
than all his sorrow.
Are you sure
you can trust the enemy?
Enemy? Is that
what you are to him?
I see two musicians
who are walking the same path.
[ Sighs ]
[ Koharu laughs ]
[ Paper flutters ]
Hiroko: Oh, wow!
That's beautiful, baby!
Good job.
Go show Nagi.
Okay. [ Giggles ]
Lookit!
[ Gasps ]
[ Giggles ]
♪♪
That boy's had
his fill of tears.
Let him smile,
in life and music alike.
Kaori: Wow.
It's so dark.
Pretty creepy, huh?
Kousei:
Well, it'd be creepier
if this weren't
such a pain in the butt.
[ Laughs ]
♪♪
[ Footsteps echoing ]
[ Door opens ]
So where's your bag?
[ Gasps ] I wonder.
It's got to be
around here somewhere.
It couldn't just
walk away.
[ Wails ]
[ Growls ]
You're lying about
the stupid bag, huh?!
It isn't here, okay?
I'm sorry.
Don't be mad.
Wait a second.
You didn't have it
this afternoon, either.
Did you
come to school today?
The doctors told me
I could have a free day
out of the hospital.
I'm sorry. I just wanted
to come here, no matter what.
'Cause I was starting
to forget it.
I'm the one
who should apologize.
This was your one day out,
and I took it up.
It should have been
Watari here, not me.
Are you
going to forget?
Huh?
The girl who brought you here
on a wild-goose chase,
the one you helped when
she found a lost little kid,
who snuck out of the hospital
and waited for a boy...
are you going to
forget her?
Part of me will echo
in their hearts forever.
In some tiny way,
these people aren't ever
going to forget about us.
I'll never forget
about us.
I'll never forget,
no matter what happens.
[ Grunts ]
I'm glad it was you,
you know?
[ Gasps ]
-Are you all right?
Yeah. A little tired.
That's all.
Kaori: Look at you riding double
on a school bike.
Kousei: Hey, it's not like
they're using it.
Sorry about
your lesson.
No big deal.
It's Hiroko,
so it'll all pan out.
For what it's worth,
I'm glad you skipped it.
I had such a wonderful time
with you this afternoon,
best I've had in a while,
so thank you.
First
we tackled the mall,
then crept through
the school at night.
Now you're taking me home
on the back of a bicycle.
Look at them twinkling up there
with all their heart.
Maybe it's the night air,
but your words
feel so warm,
like you're whispering them
in my ear.
I'll stand in for Watari
anytime gladly...
forever.
♪♪
She wept,
but I wasn't brave enough...
to ask why.
It's lagging.
You fall behind,
because you
break it up in your head.
No duh. But I'm
playing as fast as possible.
I can't go any faster.
If you're so great,
you do it.
Alright,
watch how I play.
[ Wails ]
There.
Dumb piano!
You're such a traitor!
[ Gasps ]
And you,
no fair showing off!
[ Chuckles ]
Mnh-mnh.
[ Gasps ]
You okay?
Uh, yes, sir!
I hate getting it wrong.
Great.
Let's run it one more time.
But what I really hate
is Kousei Arima.
Satsuki: Nagi, did you really
reject that upperclassman?
Komugi: How many
does that make now?
Nagi: He was a total bookworm,
not my type.
Any idea what you're
gonna do for the festival yet?
Not a clue.
The festival's
in November, Nagi.
We need to figure it out
while there's still time.
We're allowed to have guests
from outside the school,
right, like graduates?
They say Miike's
bringing in someone famous.
I have other stuff
on my mind right now.
Like revenge
and how I'm gonna get mine
against that stupid Arima.
[ Chuckles ]
What's she laughing about?!
Just leave it alone.
You know, our school
does have a reputation
for its top students
putting on
pretty spectacular performances
for this show.
And if you're not one of them,
I don't know who is.
Me, one of our best?
She's right. I'm the Angel
of Kurumi Junior High,
perfection itself!
Both: Ahh! She's a monster!
Nagi: So why does he ding me
for every little mistake!
Slow down.
Your fingers slip
because
you play it too fast.
Forte and allegro
aren't the same thing.
[ Wails ]
Nagi, wait!
Where are you going?!
Hiroko: Go get her, Teach.
Huh?
Comes with the territory.
Trust me.
[ Bird squawking ]
What am I supposed to do?
My stupid hands are too small.
[ Running footsteps ]
[ Kousei panting ]
Hiroko thought
you might be here. [ Chuckles ]
Hmph!
[ Sputters ]
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm kind of figuring out
this teaching thing as I go.
You want a snack?
Here.
Hmm.
You're bribing me
with a sweet potato?!
Just look at it,
all warm and delicious.
I bet you
it'll melt in your mouth.
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Squeals ]
Mmm!
Agh!
He totally bought me off
with a snack!
It's very pretty
out here.
Yeah, huh?
I used to play
on these steps a lot
with my favorite person
in the world.
Boy: Come on, Nagi!
You got to keep up, okay?!
Wait for me!
Nagi: The truth is he got into
playing the piano first,
so I've kind of been following
in his footsteps.
Kousei: You admire him.
Yeah, but he spends all
his time pursuing his big
rival,
and now it feels like
he's just kind of stuck,
like he doesn't even realize
how good he is.
It's the reason I play piano,
because he inspired me.
I want him to know that.
Why am I admitting
all of this to Arima?
He's a jerk-face.
[ Scoffs ]
What about my vengeance?
Huh?
I guess I play
for the wrong reason.
For what it's worth,
you wouldn't be
the first.
Maybe I wanted you to tell me
it's okay to play for him,
that I don't have to
feel bad about it.
Both: 1, 2, 3!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Let's go again!
1, 2, 3!
Now you got to tell me if
there's someone you like a lot.
Not really.
Uh-huh!
It's written
all over your face.
What kind of girl is she?
You want to know, huh?
Okay, I'll tell you.
She's the kind of girl
who already likes my friend.
I see.
And that's a good enough reason
to just give up?
[ Gasps ]
1, 2, 3.
It's pretty cliché,
you know,
friends over love.
Yeah,
you're not wrong,
but sometimes life makes
the decision for you.
Hmm.
1, 2, 3, 4...
Tell me
something about her.
She makes me feel
like I'm strapped in
to a roller coaster.
It's hard
to catch my breath.
I'm laughing and crying
all at once.
Just by being around...
[ Bow clatters ]
...she's taken my monochrome
world and filled it with
color.
She's like a firework.
throwing radiance
into the night.
Oh, hi,
Mr. Brought No Canelés!
You had one job,
Friend A, one job!
What the heck
is wrong with you?!
Watari's got
all the sugar you need.
The day has been saved.
I know why he forgot
to bring 'em today.
Word on the street
is he's teaching piano
to some first-year girl.
All: What?!
I demand
you introduce her to me!
How come you knew about this
and I didn't?!
I needed advice on how to deal
with a girl pupil.
Why would I come to you
with that?
What did you say,
you little troll!
I take it all back,
okay?!
Slipper to the face,
jerk!
Why is everybody
giving me grief about this?
Hiroko forced me to do it.
-It's lipstick!
-Huh? [ Growls ]
Tsubaki: Go on, horn-dog!
Tell us all about this girl!
What have you been
teaching her, huh?!
I never got to date
a first year!
And you really think
you have the time
to waste on all of this?
Hold on.
I just said that Hiroko --
I don't care.
Whatever lame excuse
you were about to give me,
don't bother.
If you have time for some girl,
you'd better
use it on yourself.
I work with her a bit
after school,
and then I go home and practice
my own stuff, okay?
And I'm telling you
that's not enough!
Uh...
Those hours
aren't coming back ever!
Oh, but you're
the great child prodigy.
You can just wing it,
right?!
I just told you
that I practice!
Whatever you're doing,
double it!
At least then
you're close.
The competitions start
in December, damn it!
You're running
on borrowed time as it is!
Before you know it...
[ Gasps ]
Wow. [ Chuckles ]
Where did that crazy rant
come from, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[ Playing
"Piano Sonata Number 8" ]
♪♪
[ Chuckles ]
Right about now,
a bit of my lipstick is ruining
your afternoon, Arima.
[ Sighs ]
Satsuki: You must be
having a good day, huh?
Yeah? Why is that?
Your notes sound
like they're skipping along.
Notes can't skip.
They're not alive.
Well, not if you want to get
all technical about it,
but, yeah, that's definitely
what they're doing.
She's the kind of girl
who already likes my friend.
No way is it gonna work out
for that wimp.
He doesn't have a chance.
I guess maybe...
that's a way the two of us
are the tiniest bit alike,
chasing the one person
we can never catch up with,
gazing at them
with eyes full of wonder.
For his sake,
I'll do whatever I can
to take down Kousei Arima.
A worthy sacrifice...
I'm home!
...for one who
truly deserves it.
Hey, you're back.
And kind of early, too.
I am the phantom,
the one who lurks
in the opera house.
How was your day,
big brother?
Kaori: Hey.
So what'd you bring me?
Oh! I forgot them.
Sorry.
I shouldn't make you
worry so much.
It's not very nice.
I know.
Not again.
Starting to laugh
out of nowhere.
Blowing up
over the tiniest thing.
Sobbing without warning,
then acting so sweet
before giving up
on it all.
That's how
my mom used to be.
Not again.
Please not again.
[ Sighs ]
[ Static crackles ]
Not you.
Not like this.
You're just like the book.
"You really are
a strange person.
You come to the hospital
to visit me,
and yet all this time,
you haven't said a word."
♪♪
"Want to kill yourself
with me?"
[ "Orange" playing ]
[ Singing in Japanese ]
♪♪