[AN]
You're home!
Hey. Sure am!
[AN giggles]
Wha‐‐ Whoa, take it easy!
[AN'S MOM]
You two stop that.
Hands off. Your clothes
are still dirty.
Yeah, okay. Hey, An.
We can play after
I've had a bath.
Do it as fast as you can!
[NAO'S MOM]
Other hand.
[gasps]
[NAO'S MOM] Where are you
going in the morning?
[NAO]
To the library to study.
I'm not playing that
game with you anymore.
I told you to quit the club,
so why are you still
going to practice?
I'm not.
I know you're lying.
It's true. I did quit.
I'm telling you this
for your own good,
so you need to listen.
I'm worried about you, Nao.
You shouldn't be hanging
around boys like them.
[NAO]
Mom.
Why can't you just do as I say?
[NAO'S MOM]
Fine.
I'll take this up with
your club advisor myself.
That'll solve the problem.
Maybe after that,
you'll finally stop
disobeying your mother.
What? You want to
watch Shingo's game?
[AN] Mm‐hm! Tomorrow's Sunday
so I wanna go to Shingo's
school with him and watch
him play in his match!
[AN'S MOM]
But don't you wanna go shopping
with me tomorrow?
We can go to a movie afterwards!
[AN] No! I wanna go
to school with Shingo
and watch him play!
Well, you can't.
An. Do you want to go that bad?
Yeah. I really wanna
watch Shingo's match!
Shingo. Can you look after
her if she comes along?
Of course I can.
Plus I'll have the whole club
there to help me out.
[AN'S DAD]
That should be fine, right, Mom?
I think they can handle this.
An. You be a good girl and
listen to your big brother.
‐‐Yay!
‐‐[AN'S MOM] Honey, please!
[AN'S MOM]
Honestly.
[giggles]
[AYA] They've got you going
to practice on Sundays, too?
You're working hard!
You, too, going in on
the weekend. Good for us.
[AYA] Well, a weekend off
would be nice for a change.
[sighs] What would
really be great
would be a better‐paying job.
[MAKI] I think everybody dreams
of a better paying job.
[AYA] We all need dreams
to help keep us going.
Yeah, I guess so.
[AYA] Maki. How is
soft tennis? Still fun?
[MAKI]
Mm... Mm‐hm!
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Great. Glad to hear it.
[YUTA] Aw, hi there!
Are you Shingo's sister?
Hey! An's here!
Hi, Taiyo! Doin' good?
Hey. Nice to see you again, An!
Long time no see,
An. 'Member me?
Vice‐president!
Wow, she's so smart!
I think she's got you beat.
Maybe. Already knows katakana.
Now, An, be a good girl, okay?
You're partners with my brother!
Yeah, I sure am!
[TAIYO]
Hey, An.
You wanna come help me
sweep off the tennis courts?
[AN]
Yeah! That sounds fun!
Thanks for helping us out.
And good luck with the match.
Same to you.
The girls have all been
looking forward to today,
so I'm hoping they'll have
some fun with it this time.
[SAKURA]
Okay, Namie.
They left the nurse's
office open for us,
so if anyone gets hurt,
go straight there.
Make sure everybody
stays hydrated.
It's pretty hot out here today.
[NAMIE] Yes, ma'am.
I'll let everyone know.
We're going in the same order
we talked about, right?
Hirahashi and Nagae.
Tawaramoto and Ichikawa.
Then Kuroda and Kawanishi.
And we're up last.
Sounds good.
Everyone's so excited
about this practice match.
[KEI] It felt like a real chore
the last time we did one,
but now they're all fired up.
'Cause the boys have
been practicing so hard.
[BOTH giggle]
Look here. We hold the
racket like this. See?
[AN]
Mm‐hm! That's easy.
[yelping]
Help, Shingo!
Got it. Watch this.
You're so cool!
You look at Shingo
like he's a superhero.
That's 'cause my big
brother is the strongest
in the whole world!
[GROUP laughs]
Hello, looks like we've got
a tiny little cheerleader today!
You all need to be
extra careful.
Keep an eye on her and make sure
she doesn't get hurt, okay?
We've got it, Tacky.
Everyone's taking
turns watching her;
nothing will happen.
Maki. About today's match.
Yeah?
Is it okay if I go explore?
"Oh, yeah, sure!"
[KEI] Are you okay
with five‐set matches?
Yeah, that'll be perfect.
These bags are heavy.
Why do I have to take two?
[KANAKO] Well, you are the
strongest in the whole world.
[SHINGO laughs]
Hey. Where did An go?
She needed to use the bathroom,
so I told her where it was.
‐‐I guess she's not back yet.
‐‐[SHINGO] Huh?
Wait. You let her wander off?
Why would you do that?
I can't go with her
into the girls' room.
Are you an idiot?
This is bad.
[KANAKO]
Rintaro!
[panting]
We have to go find An!
Huh?
[TAIYO]
An?
Hey, An, where did you go?
An. Come on out now!
[TSUBASA]
Where is she?
I'm worried 'cause
she's so little.
I hope she didn't
get herself stuck.
I don't think that she would.
She's smart.
[KANAKO]
We're safe. The door is locked.
That's good.
At least we know she's
not on the roof.
Hey, An?
You have club
activities on a Sunday?
If she's lost...
They'll cancel our match.
You need to stop wasting
your time on soft tennis, Nao.
It's because An is here.
[NAO]
Because of her.
[YUTA]
We couldn't find her there.
[SHINGO]
For real?
[KANAKO]
Yeah.
[SHINGO]
Then we've got nothing.
[TSUBASA]
Dammit, where'd she go?
And you?
No luck.
Really? How hard
were you looking?
You think I'm lying?
It's your fault this is
happening in the first place!
[TAIYO] Wait, I'm not trying
to accuse you of anything!
[SHINGO] No, this is my fault.
I'm really sorry, everybody.
But please. Keep looking!
Of course we're
gonna keep looking.
We'll find her.
We've already checked
everywhere dangerous.
I'm sure that An's safe.
[YUTA]
Let's keep going!
[ITSUKI]
Right. Stay sharp!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Yeah!
I'm so sorry about this.
Please give the guys
a little more time.
[TOMA] Forgive us!
It won't be much longer!
Hey, shouldn't we
have started by now?
[TENNIS STUDENT 9E]
The boys do understand that
we're trying to practice for
the summer tournament,
too, don't they?
[TAIYO] Nao. You need
to tell me the truth.
[NAO]
I am telling the truth.
I looked around for An
and I couldn't find her.
No lie.
[TAIYO] Shingo is really
worried about her.
Everybody is.
I get that.
Seriously, I don't
know where she is.
Where did you look?
[NAO] The first‐floor bathroom,
the multipurpose room,
and the nurse's office.
You went inside
and looked around?
[NAO]
Yeah. She wasn't there.
[MAKI] I went to the
nurse's office, too.
But I couldn't check it
because the door was locked.
How did you get in?
[NAO]
I looked. I'm telling you I did.
There wasn't anybody there!
Are you sure it wasn't
you who locked it?
[gasps]
Hey, what are you‐‐ Get off!
No way. Nao, what did you do?
She's fine.
[panting]
Maki...
Time to wake up.
Hey, An. Rise n' shine.
[AN grunts]
[yawns]
This is all my fault.
I let her out of my sight.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
No. As captain, it's on me.
Forgive us.
As vice president, this is
my responsibility, too.
‐‐[TAKAYUKI] Hey, boys!
‐‐[SAKURA] Guys.
There's really no need
for the begging.
This is on all of us
as club members.
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
We're sorry!
[TAKAYUKI]
Uh. This is kind of awkward.
But they're right, it's
the club's responsibility.
And mine, too.
Please forgive us.
[SAKURA]
That's enough!
[TENNIS STUDENTS laughing]
[ALL laughing]
[NAO] This isn't right.
I shouldn't be part of this.
It wasn't supposed
to be this way.
It's okay, Nao, it's over.
Everything's fine.
All of us are right here.
[grunts]
You can do it, Shingo!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
[KANAKO]
I don't understand why Tsukinose
would lie like that.
[MAKI]
I think that, in his head,
he might have been
telling us the truth.
[KANAKO]
What do you mean?
If Nao thought that
he would be better off
if the lie was true,
he could have
made himself think that it was.
[KANAKO] What would have
happened if we didn't
end up finding An when we did?
I'm sure that they would have
canceled the practice match.
I don't know if that's
what Nao was trying
to do from the start,
or if he just committed
to the lie because the guilt
of admitting the truth
would have been
too much for him.
Most people don't like to lie.
It makes them feel ashamed
and disgusted with themselves.
But if they can fool themselves
into believing their own lies,
they can get rid
of those feelings
without having
to face the truth.
At least for a while.
Sure, but in the end,
is it really worth
having to keep all that up?
He should know it'll
end up worse for him.
[YUTA] Some people lie about
random stuff for no reason.
Maybe because of emotional
stress or trauma.
[TOMA] Nao deals with plenty
of that thanks to his mom.
Anyone who knows him
could tell you.
So you think it's Nao's mom
who's causing him stress?
It's normal for parents
to worry about their kids
and get involved in
their lives, but...
The way she does it is too much.
She rejects everything about him
that doesn't line up
with what she wants.
[KANAKO]
Being that overbearing
is a kind of child
abuse all by itself.
[MAKI] But parents who act
like that tell themselves
that they're looking out for
their children's interests.
They don't even understand
what they're really
doing to their kids.
Do you think Nao's dad ever
says anything about it?
There's no way he's thinking
that much about his family.
[TOMA] We had an awesome
practice today, though.
[YUTA] Yeah, it was cool
of the girls to let us play
against their
third‐year regulars.
[MAKI] They were pretty
tough, but now we know
where we need to improve.
Think you can win a real match?
I think we don't have a choice.
[JUN] You having fun
over there, Tsubasa?
[TSUBASA]
I guess?
[YOU] You seem pretty
fired up the past few weeks.
At least when you're
fiddling with your racket.
[TSUBASA]
Do I?
Is playing soft tennis really
that much fun for you?
The ball's all squishy. Like
can you even feel the hits?
Yeah, way more than in a sport
you play with your feet.
[JUN] Who wants to play
a sport with tools?
[YOU]
Right? How sad.
Oh, so it's the tools
you don't like?
You know they're what
separates us from the animals.
Ha! Know what? Fine!
I'll be an animal if I
can still play soccer!
And a ball is a tool, isn't it?
Yeah! A ball's a tool!
You two are brilliant
at being stupid.
[ALL laugh]
Still playing your fake sport?
[TSUBASA]
What about it?
I can play whatever
sport I want.
[TSUBASA'S DAD]
Seriously?
Wait a minute, Tsubasa!
What was that attitude about?
Answer me!
It was about you always
talking down to me!
Let go, Asshole!
[grunts]
[crashing]
[snap]
[gasps]
[JUN]
Tsubasa! Are you okay?
[YOU]
Did you fall?
[TSUBASA'S MOM] What happened
here? Are you all right?
Do you need an ambulance?
No. It's fine.
[YOU]
Wait! Where are you going?
[JUN]
Tsubasa!
[AN]
Your school was super fun!
I'm glad. But you scared me.
Don't run off alone like that.
Can you say you're sorry?
Sorry, Shingo.
Okay. And if you wanna
go exploring again
you'll ask first. Promise?
[AN]
Promise!
[AN giggling]
[AN'S MOM]
Stop squirming.
It's hard to clean your ears
when you're moving around.
[AN]
I can't help it! It tickles!
[SHINGO] I'm gonna go take
some practice swings.
The tournament is soon, right?
Keep it up, son.
[SHINGO]
Got it.
Keep it up!
[SHINGO]
Right.
Tsubasa? Come back!
[TSUBASA groans]
Hey, what happened? You're hurt!
[TSUBASA]
It's not a big deal.
Lemme see it.
[SHINGO] That looks bad.
What happened to you?
I just fell down like
half a flight of stairs.
C'mon, I've got you.
[SHINGO]
I'll be right back!
Dad! It's Tsubasa, he's hurt!
We need to get him
to the hospital!
You mean Soga?
[DOCTOR 9A] Minor ulnar
fracture. See it there?
So it's broken? How long
will it take to heal?
[DOCTOR 9A] I'd say probably
about two months.
It looks like all your weight
must have come down on it wrong.
You say you fell
down the stairs?
Uh, yeah, that's right.
I lost my footing.
Is that the truth?
Sure there wasn't
anybody else involved?
No, just me. I do stupid
things sometimes.
Huh?
[SHINGO] Doctor? Is this
going to keep him
from playing tennis?
[DOCTOR 9A]
Are you right‐handed?
Yes.
Then I'm afraid so.
You're not gonna be able to hold
a racket until it's healed.
[gasps] Two months...
[TSUBASA]
Shingo. I'm sorry.
[AN'S DAD]
Well, An's asleep.
[AN'S MOM] That's one good
part of him being out.
The house is quieter
and so is she.
[AN'S DAD]
I suppose.
That child looks so
much like his mother.
Has the exact same eyes.
I guess.
I can see it more every day.
Boys are like that.
[AN'S DAD]
Ya think?
People have always
told me that his aunt
looks like me, though.
[AN'S DAD sighs]
Where did he run off to?
He and Soga went
to the park to talk.
Why the park, at this hour?
[AN'S DAD]
They needed privacy.
[TSUBASA]
I think my dad hates me.
I'm not good enough,
and I can't keep up
with my older brothers.
[SHINGO]
That's tough competition.
They're both crazy good
at soccer, right?
Why didn't you go that route?
[TSUBASA] I never had
much talent for soccer.
I tried my best back
in elementary school.
Yeah, I was there.
We played on the
same team back then.
Dude. You were great!
I was nothing special.
There was no way I could
play on my brothers' level.
So I gave up on it,
and I don't think Dad
ever forgave me for that.
He thinks I'm a coward.
Unmanly. Totally useless.
[SHINGO] Did your dad used
to be a soccer player?
Yeah, he was.
He still brags about
it all the time.
But why does that mean
I have to do it, too?
I don't need to be
like my brothers.
I'm my own person! And today...
When I fell down
the stairs, he...
...just stood there
staring at me!
[TSUBASA]
Dammit! He did this!
I wanna play in our tournament!