[MISAKI CROWD] Go, go, Misaki!
Fight, fight, Misaki!
Win, win, Misaki!
Go, go, Misaki!
Fight, fight, Misaki!
Win, win, Misaki!
Holy crap.
What the hell are they
doing, yelling like that?
They have over 60 members
on the Misaki boys team,
so a lot of times, their first
years act as a cheer squad.
Wow. That's creepy.
Hey, Mitsue.
You might try keeping those
kinds of thoughts to yourself.
Mind your own business.
Just like we talked about.
Nao and Taiyo. You two
will be playing first.
I'm still nervous.
What if they're so far
beyond our level
that we can't even
put up a fight?
Yeah, it would seriously
suck if they shut us out.
If you think like that,
you might psych yourselves
into losing a match
you could win.
You really think they can win?
Yuta's been scouting their
team for the past week,
and he gathered a lot
of good info we can use.
Manager. What can you
tell Nao and Taiyo
about the guys they're playing?
I don't know how helpful
it'll really be.
Have a little confidence.
Let's see. You're going
to have Kazumi Miwa
setting up in the back,
and Ayumu Ooi
will be playing forward.
Miwa has a really
strong opening serve.
His shots are fast, and he
has great placement, too.
Getting shots past Ooi
won't be easy either.
These two are a classic example
of a front‐back pair.
So their basic strategy
will be what you'd expect.
Watch for Miwa to try
and set the pace.
[MAKI]
Thanks a lot, Yuta.
I think the way to win
is for both of you
to focus on making Miwa
chase after your returns.
I don't think I can keep up
with somebody on his level.
Yeah, true. You probably can't.
You didn't need to say it
like that, Katsuragi.
But you don't have to.
[TAIYO, NAO gasp]
[MAKI] Between the two of you,
he'll have plenty to deal with.
So just play the way you play.
Yeah, that strategy they
used before could work.
Why not?
These two can win this
match. Right, guys?
[SHINGO]
We got this!
Because we're badasses!
Now check out this victory dance
my little sister
and I came up with!
A victory dance? For real?
Yeah, we raise up
our right hands.
Hey, I said "we," you guys!
You, too, Yuta!
I believe that we will win!
Whoa. Fight! Okay, now you!
Okay.
Fight!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Whoa! Fight!
[SHINGO]
Go! Go! Go! Go!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB] Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Whoa! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
[KADOWAKI] Is that some
pre‐match ritual of theirs?
Apparently.
A war dance, but for
grasshoppers. I guess.
Ugh. Neck's so damn stiff.
So, we're all on the same page?
No worries, Arashi, we got this.
We won't give up a single
point to these guys.
For real, I don't even know
if we can get a proper
warm‐up out of 'em.
Maybe a stretch.
[KAZUMI] Face up.
We don't care who serves.
Do what you wanna.
We're taking this side.
[NAO] The dance actually
limbered me up.
[TAIYO] My nerves aren't
nearly as bad after that.
Let's go! You've got
this, you two!
Service side: Shijo Minami,
Ishigami and Tsukinose.
Receiving side: Misaki
Academy, Miwa and Ooi.
Five‐game match. Play ball!
[sighs]
[KAZUMI]
Come on, bring it.
[TAIYO grunts]
Ah, His serve's not bad.
[KAZUMI]
Crap!
Got it!
[grunts]
Hey, look.
They're both hanging back!
[KAZUMI]
No!
Did they just score first?
I think they did.
Oh‐‐ Not bad!
Tch.
Ugh. That was a fluke.
Uh, 1‐0!
[TAIYO grunts]
[KAZUMI]
It's the same play.
Damn!
[MISAKI MEMBER 6A]
They both stay on the baseline
and try to rally.
[MISAKI MEMBER 6B]
Yeah, and they're doing
a good job of it, too.
[gasps]
[MISAKI CROWD]
Whoa...
‐‐[YUTA] Another point!
‐‐[SHIDO] Yes!
[SHIDO]
Guys, keep it up!
Settle down, everyone,
there's still a game going on!
I can tell your kids
are giving this
everything they've got.
Yep. They sure are.
Be brave!
Be bold! To...
[BOTH]
...victory!
[KAZUMI]
Dammit!
[panting]
2‐0!
[grunts]
[KAZUMI]
Damn southpaw!
[grunts]
[KAZUMI pants]
[gasps]
[KAZUMI]
These Shijo Minami clowns!
[gasps]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]\\
Out!
You moron.
Wanna try hitting the ball?
How can I when they keep
lobbing it over me?
By moving over to where
they're hitting it, ya genius!
I am moving!
This is turning
into a train wreck.
Don't start fighting, you guys.
[BOTH]
Be brave, be bold, victory!
[grunts]
[NAO]
Gotcha!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
Out! Change sides!
[MISAKI CROWD gasps]
They're playing
like total idiots.
You guys.
We just took a game
off Misaki Academy!
Hell yeah!
[ITSUKI] It might have been a
fluke, but it's still awesome.
What happened? Did we win? Hey!
[YUTA]
Yeah!
Then, does that mean
the match is over?
No, not just yet.
This one was only
the first game.
Oh, that's right.
And they said that this was
a five‐game match, didn't they?
So how do you win then?
In soft tennis, the first
team to get four point
wins the game.
And since they're
playing a five‐game set,
that means whichever
team is able
to take three games
wins the whole match.
So, we have to do
that two more times?
Yeah. You have to
win the majority
of the games in the set,
so in a three‐game match,
you need to win two.
Seems like a complicated
way to score things.
That's just the way they
do it in soft tennis.
They'll be playing
harder after this.
They know we're for real.
[KAZUMI]
My bad.
Don't worry about it.
Let's reset.
[KAZUMI]
Yeah.
We know that we're the
better players here.
[KAZUMI] For sure. Time to
treat this like a real game.
Right. Let's do it.
Pull it together.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
Game score: 0‐1.
[sighs]
Huh?
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
Out!
What was that?
It's a slice.
He's adding sidespin.
You could've done that earlier.
1‐0!
Ah!
He started going in
with slice serves
right out of the gate.
He can consistently
pull those off?
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
2‐0!
[TAIYO]
Again?
[NAO] Will this next
one be a slice, too?
[AYUMU grunts]
Did they catch up?
Yeah, it's even now.
The game score is now one‐all.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
Game score is 2‐1.
[panting]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
Out!
They're totally
controlling the pace now.
In the end, they're still
a championship team.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6A]
Game and set!
Miwa and Ooi from
Misaki win the match
with a score of
three games to one.
Sorry. We gave it all we had.
They're on another level.
Nah, you guys did great.
Taking that first game
really threw them off guard.
Yeah. And the two
back formation works.
It'll be awesome with some
more practice. One thing‐‐
We've got some work to do
on our conditioning,
too, don't we?
True. We're gonna need
to run more often.
[RINTARO] Either way,
that was amazing, guys!
You were keeping up with
them for the first half!
[TAIYO, NAO giggle]
What do they look so
happy for? They lost.
But it was worth it.
Even if they didn't
win the game,
it taught them a lot,
and that's what matters
in a practice match.
A loss is still a loss.
[YUTA]
The tall one plays back.
His name's Yanagishita.
He's a true power hitter.
His serve is even
faster than Miwa's.
Ikeda has a great serve,
too, and he's an expert
at positioning himself to
set up Yanagishita's shots.
Between the two of them,
I can't see any weaknesses.
[RINTARO] In other words, these
guys are gonna be really good.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
Serving side: Misaki Academy,
Yanagishita and Ikeda.
On the receiving side:
Shijo Minami, Futsu and Ameno.
This is a five‐game
match. Play ball!
[RINTARO]
That's fast!
[grunts]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
Out! Game! Change sides!
We can bring it back now that
we have a chance to serve.
Plus we've got a better idea
of what kind of speed
they're working with.
That's true.
And I think Takada's
serves were way scarier.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, they're no big deal.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
Game score, 0‐1!
Let's, go!
[RINTARO]
Their left is open!
[RINTARO grunts]
All right, get 'em!
Good shot, guys!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
1‐0!
[RINTARO]
Take that!
[YANAGISHITA]
Got it!
[grunts]
[YANAGISHITA grunts]
[ITSUKI]
Careful!
Ugh. Why are they winning when
they're playing like trash?
On it!
[grunts]
‐‐[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B] Game!
‐‐You guys nailed it!
‐‐[TSUBASA] Yeah!
‐‐[TAIYO] This is awesome!
We just took another game, guys!
Rintaro looks great out there.
He's good.
I think he might have
the best game sense
out of anyone in the club.
[gasps]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
Game score, one all!
Gotcha!
[panting]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
Out!
[ITSUKI] Yuta was right,
these two are crazy good.
[RINTARO] The ball's
starting to feel heavy.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6B]
Out!
Yanagishita and Ikeda from
Misaki Academy win the match,
with a game score
of three to one.
[MISAKI MEMBER 6A]
We took the set.
[MISAKI MEMBER 6B]
But we dropped another game.
Ah. That's two games
they've managed
to take off us now. Not bad.
[SHINGO]
Guess it's our turn, huh?
[TSUBASA]
Yeah, and it's about time, too.
This is new.
I've never seen 'em
this worked up.
Hey, hold this for me, Taiyo.
Oof. That's heavy!
Okay, Yuta, So what's
the scoop on these guys?
[YUTA] You'll be playing
Masato Nagano at the back
and Takeru Tanaka in front.
These two were one
of the pairs who played
in Misaki's
championship tournament.
But, all I know is
they're good. Sorry.
They're good?
I could have guessed that.
[YUTA] Before you play.
You should rehydrate.
Good idea.
Yeah, thanks man.
‐‐[TSUBASA] All right.
‐‐[SHINGO] That's good!
That was some good timing.
Cheers.
It's go time, bro!
Woo!
Cool. It's our call.
We wanna serve first.
Heh. Then we'll be
taking this side,
so let's hurry it up.
Don't make this take
longer than it has to.
What do you mean by that?
Look, you know our teammates
have been holding
back, don't you?
Yeah, we're not gonna
play with our food
the way those guys did.
We're your food?
You're out of your league.
That's just how it goes.
Oh, really? That's cool.
Well, may the best pair win!
[TAKERU]
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[TSUBASA]
Good luck, have fun!
[MASATO yells]
[chuckles] That's a good start.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6C]
Serving side: Shijo Minami,
Takenouchi and Soga.
Receiving side: Misaki Academy,
Tanaka and Nagano.
Five‐game match. Play ball!
[laughs] Y'all ready for this?
Galactica Magnum Serve!
[screams]
[ARASHI laughs] Holy crap that
was the funniest damn thing
I've ever seen, you guys!
Super Revolution Cannon Serve!
Take it!
Uh!
They're already up
by two points!
I like the strategy
they thought up.
Why is this working
on them? Honestly.
Those morons are letting
themselves get rattled.
And go!
[yells]
Sha‐boom!
Uh‐‐!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6C]
Out!
That seriously won them a game.
No joke, they're the only people
who could pull off
a plan that dumb.
Sure are. They're
using their heads!
Are they really, though?
You guys're killin'
it out there!
It's all you!
It's a good start.
[SHINGO]
Yeah, we're doin' this!
[TSUBASA]
Hey, hey, hey!
Are they idiots?
What?!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6C]
Fault!
That was great, you two!
There're no rules
against screaming.
[TAKERU]
What's these guys' deal?
[yells]
‐‐[NAO] Whoa!
‐‐[TAIYO] Wow!
Nice!
Tanaka, get it together.
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm not gonna fall
for that crap anymore.
[TAKERU grunts]
What are you morons doing?
Don't let them
catch up with you!
Keep it up and we win.
Good, because Arashi
is going to beat
the crap out of us if we lose.
Yeah he is.
[ball thudding]
Crap!
‐‐[TAKERU] Nagano!
‐‐[MASATO] I'm on it!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6C]
The game score is 3‐1.
Misaki Academy, Tanaka and
Nagano are the winners!
That was super close.
They're all bark and no bite.
Well, that sucks.
They looked pretty good
for a while there.
[SHINGO] Damn, the shock‐and‐awe
strategy wasn't enough
to get us through the whole set.
Yeah, I think we'd
need more prep time
to compete with a team
on their level.
In other words, all we
need is more practice.
Exactly. So let's
keep at it, right?
Man, those two are good.
I'm glad you caught
onto that. Maki.
[MAKI] And they're only
gonna get better from here.
[BOTH]
Ah!
Looks like it's down to us.
Yuta!
Right!
You're going to be playing
against Arashi Oji
in the back and
Shinjiro Sunaga in front.
These two are the best players
Misaki Academy has.
Which means that you two
are about to get wrecked.
That's no fun.
I also did a little bit
of research myself.
What I found out
about these guys
is that Oji will be the
one calling the shots.
He's basically the leader.
And now I see.
It's time.
Yup. Be back in a second!
Don't worry, you two,
you've got this!
‐‐Let's see your stuff!
‐‐[RINTARO] You can do it!
Win at least one!
Yeah, you gotta take a game
no matter what, guys!
Give 'em hell, boys! Yeah!
I've got to admit,
I wasn't expecting
your kids to be anywhere
near this hyped up.
Honestly, I'm just
as surprised as you.
What kind of pep talk
did you give 'em?
I can't take credit for this.
All right, I understand
if you don't wanna
reveal your secrets,
but Oji and Sunaga
are the best we've got.
So this should be fun to watch.
Your best? They're
not third‐years?
[KADOWAKI]
Did you not know?
Of course I did.
These guys are our best, too.
Don't think winning a few games
means that you're good.
My teammates underestimated you,
and that's all on them.
Don't expect me to
make that mistake.
They're gonna have to
mop you off my court!
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
What's that about?
Serving side: Shijo Minami,
Shinjo and Katsuragi.
Receiving side: Misaki Academy,
Oji and Sunaga.
Five‐game match. Play ball!
[ARASHI] He may be a scrub,
but his serve is... fast!
[ARASHI]
Whoa!
Hey, That was great!
Well, it was a nice serve!
This might end up
being fun after all.
[grunts]
That was fast.
They turned it around.
They're unreal.
These guys are beasts.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
1‐2!
Fault!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Double fault!
Maki.
Just relax.
My bad.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Change sides!
Game score is 1‐0!
We're barely gettin' started.
[ARASHI]
Now let's have some real fun!
Shit!
Hey. What's up?
You can do better
than this, right?
Keep talkin'.
[MAKI]
I can see it!
[MAKI grunts]
Man, that's fast.
Yeah, because I'm awesome.
If my first serve
stays in bounds,
there's no way you're
ever gonna hit it back!
Not friggin' possible!
[gasps]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Out!
So close!
That serve is insane, though.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
3‐0!
[grunts]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Change service!
Jeez, this is a monster pair.
Both players have got
some sick serves.
There's not a lot we can do
except hope they hit it out.
This Arashi guy's
serves are way faster
than anything our club members
have had to face before.
It's hard to even make
contact with the ball.
Why are you talking
like they can't win?
Hey, listen.
I thought of something
I think we should try.
[TOMA gasps]