[AYA] I bet there won't be
any chocolate‐covered critters
in a place like this.
[MAKI] That's one chore
I won't have to worry about.
I'm fine with that.
Look, we even have an elevator.
We're on the eighth floor
this time, right?
This move is gonna
take us a while.
I'll just take the stairs.
[AYA]
Hang on, Maki!
You'll work yourself to
death climbing all those.
I'll be fine, Mom.
It's nothing new.
Maki!
That kid of yours
moves pretty quick.
We didn't have an elevator
before, so he's used to it.
[GROUP] Let's go, Shijo!
Fight, fight, Shijo!
Let's go, Shijo! Fight, fight!
Well, what do we have here?
The two soft tennis
teams are having
a pretty one‐sided
practice match.
Really? It's the boys
versus the girls?
Are they seriously
trying to play against
the national champions?
Those boys are
gonna get destroyed!
For real!
[BOTH laugh]
Yeah, go ahead and laugh.
But, it's kind of sad.
'Cause, they really
are getting destroyed.
[grunts]
I mean, at least they're all
doing their best, yeah?
Ah!
Huh?
[laughs] Wow, you
scored on me good!
Come on!
He really is doing
his best, I swear!
He's just nervous!
[ITSUKI]
And... There!
Aw, well, dang it.
That shot went by way too fast.
There's no way either
of us could've gotten it.
That deserves a
round of applause.
Yeah, you're right. Nice.
[TAKAYUKI] Wait! They're not
trying to be mean! Honest!
Yeah! They're not trying
to do much of anything!
[TSUBASA]
Whoa!
[giggles] Look at
that! It got stuck!
They're so pathetic. This
hardly counts as practice.
Yeah, that's a fair point.
At least your girls
can take it easy.
[GROUP] Let's go, Takada!
Fight, fight, Takada!
Let's go, Takada!
[grunts]
I got it!
Ah!
Thanks for the match.
I learned a lot
from playing you.
Glad to hear it.
Work on your first
serve's placement,
and you won't be
half bad, Shinjo.
Right. Thanks for the tip.
Speaking of.
Are you okay with me speeding
up my second serve a bit?
Yeah, sure.
As long as it doesn't
affect your accuracy,
it's fine by me.
[TENNIS STUDENT 1B]
Way to go, Kei!
[TENNIS STUDENT 1C]
Good game out there, you two!
Why are we wasting
our practice time
playing against the boys' team?
We're doing them a favor.
And they should be
grateful that we even
agreed to these matches
in the first place.
[GROUP]
But they're not.
[TENNIS STUDENT 1F]
What's wrong with them?
[TENNIS STUDENT 1G] They don't
even care that they lost!
Hey, Captain. Uh. Good effort!
Yeah right. I sucked.
Here I thought
Toma'd get a game
off the Black Butterfly.
I guess he's just as bad
as the rest of us.
[TSUBASA] Hey, Itsuki, The
White Butterfly's your sister,
isn't she? So, tell her to
go easy on us or something.
Do you honestly think she
would even listen to me?
That's fair. I guess not.
Must be nice having an
older sister who's smart,
pretty, and athletic.
I'm kinda jealous of you.
You cannot be serious.
Wha...? Uh. No. Of course not.
Good to know. Because if
you were, you'd be dead.
[RINTARO]
Okay, Itsuki, that's enough!
Don't wanna bring down
the team morale!
Well, it's not like
we're ever gonna win.
So, who cares?
Even if that's true,
you don't have to be
so harsh about it.
But it is true.
We're never gonna be good,
so it doesn't matter
how hard we try.
But y'know, I heard that
Ms. Muroi practically begged
Mr. Sakurai to have
a practice game.
She thought that we would
be a nice change of pace.
[SHINGO]
Wait. Are you for real?
Shingo. Nao is just
making stuff up again.
Aw. That sucks.
[TAKUTO] I'm sick of this.
I'm tired of losing!
Uh‐‐ Takuto?
This is a club
for losers anyway!
Don't you get it?
[gasps]
How could anyone get
popular when they're stuck
in a stupid Soft
Tennis Club like this?
Nanase's never gonna
like me if I'm some loser!
Hang on a sec.
[TOMA]
You mean that Nanase?
Never gonna happen.
I'm gonna start doing
things that are cool!
Like, playing normal tennis!
Then I'm gonna become
popular and stuff!
You'll see!
I don't think that's
how it works, man.
[TAKUTO]
You can't stop me!
I'm quitting this club
and I'm gonna be cool
and popular starting now‐‐!
[TAKUTO yells]
You do that.
All club activities
at this school
operate with the funds
provided directly
by the administration.
As you might expect,
the amount of support
that each club gets,
is something we take seriously.
Naturally, there is a
slight variance in how much
is provided to
each of the clubs.
The total number of students
enlisted is a factor,
for example.
The problem is, this equal
distribution of funds
naively assumes that all
clubs have the same value.
It fails to consider
the amount of effort
and passion invested in them.
So, as your current
student council president.
I want to change all of that.
I'd like to implement
a system that compensates
each club according to
their level of commitment
and quality of results.
That will be truly fair.
I believe hard work
and enthusiasm
will always produce
great results.
In that same vein,
those results deserve
a proportional reward.
Unfortunately, there
are some clubs which
produce no results and
needlessly drain funds
that are better used elsewhere.
These sorts of clubs
are worse than useless.
They are essentially stealing
resources from others
who deserve it more.
So, why should these clubs
continue to exist at all?
[TSUBASA]
Who does she think she is? What?
So we have to win in order
to be considered a real club?
But they won't go
through with it, right?
I thought these clubs
were supposed to be about
students enjoying themselves.
It's already starting
to happen, man.
Just take a look at the
clubs that were good enough
to go to nationals.
They've all got their
funds secured already.
Then what about us?
What's goin' to happen
to the Soft Tennis Club?
Unless we win a match
in the summer tournament,
it's over.
Student Council Pres
sure is heartless.
She knows that we're not
good enough to win anything.
It's been four years of
nothing but losses, hasn't it?
Guess we're done for.
[RINTARO]
Don't be like that, guys!
[ITSUKI] So, what are we
all gonna do next semester?
Well, I suppose my mom
did always want me
to learn how to play an
instrument of some kind.
Is it too late to
join a music club?
We're really disbanding?
But think about the members
that came before us.
You know that it's
their fault, too.
They didn't really
do us any favors.
We shouldn't feel
too bad about it.
Yeah, good point. No
third years stuck around.
And we also weren't able
to get any first years
to join us this year either.
It's just us second years now,
at the very end.
That's too bad.
I gotta figure out what I'm
gonna do with my old racket.
Well, I could always
give it to my sister.
Not sure she'd have
use for it though.
[ALL gasp]
You've gotta be kidding.
[MAKI]
Good morning!
Oh! Good morning!
[AYA] Ah, crap!
Where is it, where is it?
[AYA]
Found you!
[MAKI]
Mom! Food's ready!
Oh, you're the best, Maki!
I gotta hurry!
[gasps]
Come on.
[MAKI]
Here you go!
Thanks! You're a lifesaver.
[MAKI] No problem. You've
got everything now, right?
[RYOMA]
Toma.
Do me a favor? Hand this
book off to Maki.
Huh? Did you say...?
[gasps]
Hey! Watch where you're going!
[MAKI]
Uh‐‐
I'm sorry! You're
not hurt are you?
I, um. Well, no.
I just got a bit startled
when you ran past me, so.
I'll be more careful next time.
Uh, aren't you the guy
who came by to meet
your neighbors yesterday?
Oh, yeah, you live downstairs.
I'm Kanako Mitsue from unit 701.
Right, that's what
it was. Mornin'.
You're Maki Katsuragi?
Did I get that right?
Yeah. Nice to meet you.
[KANAKO] Wait. Why didn't
you take the elevator?
It's just kind of a hassle.
Yeah? And how is
running up and down
eight flights of stairs
not a hassle to you?
Who's the new kid?
I wonder which school
his uniform is from.
[KANAKO]
Ugh. Man, I really hate math.
I like math.
Huh?
Been a while.
Hang on. You're Toma Shinjo!
Oh. Looks like you
guys are already
familiar with each other.
This place is my home again.
[KANAKO]
Uh...
So, uh. What is this?
It's from Ryoma.
Your brother?
Uh‐‐ Ah! Wow!
An Astronomical Almanac!
An Astronomical what now?
It's basically a bunch of data
on the stars and planets.
Check it out.
[KANAKO] Oh, gross.
This is nothing but numbers.
So he's an old friend of yours?
[TOMA] Yesterday,
the student council decided
to apportion club
activity funds based on
achievements by majority vote.
This is effective immediately
So what?
That means the boys'
Soft Tennis Club
is gonna get shut down.
[YUTA] That explains why Shinjo
was in such a bad mood.
Next, we have a new
transfer student.
If you notice him struggling
with any of the coursework,
please don't hesitate
to help him out.
Don't worry about me!
I'll be just fine on my own.
[TENNIS STUDENT 1E] What do
think the boys are gonna do?
[TENNIS STUDENT 1G]
I saw some of them trying
to recruit new members today.
Yeah?
I heard they wanna find
athletic people to join.
That way, they might
have a chance
at winning something.
[TENNIS STUDENT 1E]
Well, they're not gonna get any
new members with
that sorry attitude.
[TENNIS STUDENT 1G]
I wish they'd stop.
They're making soft
tennis look bad.
[TOMA]
Dammit. Is there nobody left?
Seems like all the
athletes have joined
other sports clubs
already. So what now?
[STUDENT 1DD]
Ah, crap, it went that way!
Here it comes!
Grab it already!
[CAT 1A meows]
Over there!
‐‐After it!
‐‐[CAT 1A meows]
It's too damn fast!
Don't let it get away!
Maki! Look at that kitty go!
What? You've never
seen a cat before?
‐‐[KANAKO] I gotta get this.
‐‐[STUDENT 1GG] There!
[STUDENT 1DD]
Get it!
[STUDENT 1C]
It's here!
‐‐[KANAKO] This is great.
‐‐[STUDENT 1FF] You little!
[yelps]
[STUDENTS]
Whoa!
[meowing]
How did a little cat
like you get inside
of a place like this?
[YUTA] Hey, Shinjo. That friend
of yours is something else.
Is that...?
Katsuragi. I'll get
straight to the point.
Join the Soft Tennis Club.
What are you talking about?
I'm not interested in
joining any clubs right now.
Please join the club.
I don't wanna.
If we don't win at least
one match this summer,
they'll force the Soft
Tennis Club to disband.
I know you have the talent.
If we practiced
and played together,
then we might have a chance.
My answer's still "no."
Sorry, man.
Hey. Shinjo sounded pretty
desperate back there.
Yeah, I guess. I'm not
interested, though.
If you say so.
But, I feel like you're
hiding something.
I could say the exact
same thing about you.
[TOMA]
I'm trying to get Katsuragi
to join the Soft Tennis Club.
[RYOMA]
Oh, yeah? That's a great idea.
He did just transfer
to your school.
He could make some
new friends this way.
Sure, but that's
not really the reason
why I want him to join.
If we don't win a single match
at the summer tournament,
we're disbanded.
That so?
You're okay with that?
But aren't you an alumnus?
When you played for the
club, our school's team
made it all the way
to the nationals.
And you want me to
say that I don't want
the club to die?
It's your time.
And it's up to your generation
to do what you think is best.
An alumni like me shouldn't
have any say in the matter.
[TOMA] Because you think
I'm gonna fail?
No matter how hard I try?
That's not...
[TOMA]
Whatever.
Wait.
[door slams]
[TOMA]
I'm heading out.
[TOMA'S MOM] Ryoma, would
you like some breakfast?
Nah, it's okay.
I'm good with just my usual
morning coffee right now.
Well then, do you
know what you'd like
to eat for dinner tonight?
I'm actually meeting up
with a friend later,
so I won't be home
for dinner. Sorry.
Right.
And your father is out
on a business trip,
so he's gone, too.
It's just me and that boy.
Y'know, Mom. Toma isn't‐‐
But he isn't anything
like you, Ryoma!
He's different!
Don't say that.
I can't help it. Whenever
I'm around him... I just...
[schoolbell ringing]
Dang it, I'm totally
gonna miss the event
if I don't get this
picture uploaded soon!
[MAKI]
The moon and Venus.
That's a good shot.
This again? Gimme a break.
Comin' through.
Guess I'm going this way.
Hey, can you not take a hint?
I'm still waiting for you to
join the Soft Tennis Club.
Like I told you yesterday,
I don't have any
interest in joining
your little sports thing.
I know about your mom.
She works full‐time right?
[YUTA] Katsuragi's father
isn't in the picture anymore.
His parents got a divorce
and his mom took custody.
It happened when he
was just a little kid,
and it's been the two of
them living on their own
ever since then.
I already knew that.
And I remember that
his last name
actually used to be "Kyobate."
Okay. Well, did you know
that he takes care
of all the house
chores by himself?
Wait. All of them?
Yeah. The cooking,
laundry, and cleaning.
He does it all on his own.
[YUTA] Since his mom
is too busy working,
he's the only one around
who can run the errands.
So what?
If you need any help,
I can give you a
hand after practice.
Mind your own business.
The place his mom works at
is a small construction firm.
I assume she works
as an architect there.
And that particular company
isn't a very big one.
So it's possible that he doesn't
have the financial support,
which would prevent him from
joining a club like yours.
Let go.
Don't worry about your
tennis equipment or uniform.
I'll take care of it for you.
You won't have to spend
any of your own money.
I said the money isn't
going to be a problem!
Wow. So, you can solve
all of your problems
by throwing some money
around. Must be nice.
[TOMA] My brother used
to be in the club, y'know!
That's right, I remember.
[MAKI] He had that racket back
when he was in middle school.
He was in the Soft Tennis
Club. That explains it.
Y'know, Ryoma approved
of you joining the club,
and even thought you'd do well.
In that case...
Uh?
I'll join the club.
But only if you pay me.
Uh‐‐
Aw, what's the matter?
I'm not made of free time.
But paid time is something
that I can get behind.
I'll charge you
for manual labor.
Unlike you, money is
actually a problem for me.
So I don't join clubs
just for fun.
But this might be
too much for you.
I figured.
So. I guess we're done here.
Ten thousand yen a month!
That makes 30K in total.
Sound good? And if we
win at the tournament,
I'll throw in a bonus!
Making it 40K overall!
Huh?
If that's not enough, I can
pay you even more! Okay?
Uh‐‐
You are good with that. Right?
Ah, that's great! Let's shake
on it so it's official!
Welcome to the club!
Huh?
After school tomorrow,
come to the locker room
that's by the tennis courts!
I'll have a uniform
and racket for you.
We'll start right away!
We'll begin with the basics
and then we can move on to‐‐
Hang on. Slow down.
Oh, yeah!
First things first. Take this.
It's a solid racket that's
great for beginners.
I'm sure you can handle it.
You'll be playin' like
a pro in no time! Here!
Hey, uh. I dunno if I can‐‐
'Kay! See ya!
[MAKI]
Uh. The heck was that?
I didn't actually
agree to anything yet.
The Soft Tennis Club.
[doorbell rings]
Coming!
[MAKI]
What the‐‐?
[gasps]
Hey, what's up?
Long time no see.
How you holdin' up?
It's been what? Two months?
So this is your
new place, huh?
Damn. It's small.
And as usual, there isn't much.
Please. Get out of here.
What did you just say
to me, you little brat?
You can't talk to
your dad like that.
Show some respect.
Get up. Gimme the usual.
I came by for a withdrawal.
Now, where is it?
[MAKI]
We don't have any money.
[MAKI gasps]
[MAKI groans]
Sure you don't.
There's gotta be some
emergency savings hidden
in one of the obvious
spots around here.
But your mother wouldn't
hide things from me.
That means you did.
You must think you're so clever.
[KENJI]
Hm...
All right. I'll be
borrowing this.
Tell your mom I said hello.