[knocking]
You had club activities
on a Sunday?
What was that all about?
I already explained
it yesterday.
The team went to a barbeque.
I don't believe that.
A club full of irresponsible
boys having a random barbecue?
Something just isn't adding up.
I wouldn't say that
they're irresponsible.
[NAO'S MOM] Regardless, those
boys on the Soft Tennis Club
are a bad influence on you.
And besides, you're not
even old enough to drink,
so what fun is
a barbecue to you?
In any case,
you should be spending
more time on your studies,
or else you won't pass those
high school entrance exams.
It's only my second
year, you know.
So, there's one year left!
And all that soft tennis
is wasting the time
you have remaining.
You need to quit
before it's too la‐‐
I'm not going to quit!
[NAO'S MOM]
Not sure if you forgot,
but I watched one of
your practice matches.
Your advisor even
thought it was a joke.
All of those
"teammates" of yours
never stood a chance
and lost every game.
And you couldn't hold your
own out on the court either.
I've never been
so embarrassed before.
Yeah, but now
things are different.
[NAO'S MOM]
How exactly? Are you winning?
Is that why you're
slacking off at some party?
[NAO]
Well, I‐‐
[NAO'S MOM]
Just do as you're told!
I'm only telling you these
things for your own good!
It's my responsibility
as your mother!
But did I ask for that?
No, I didn't.
[TAKAYUKI] Tsukinose's parents
actually said that?
Mr. Sakurai.
Claims like these can
often be hard to disprove.
It's important that
you understand
this type of situation.
So, unless we do
something promptly,
the state of things could
escalate and get out of hand.
I assume you want to
discipline the club then.
[PRINCIPAL] I do believe
that's our best option
at the moment, but...
Maybe it is the best option
for the school and the parents.
But then... What about the kids?
What's best for them?
Huh? Seriously? An entire week?
For real? How come? Why now?
Well, I can think of one reason.
Was it that old hag?
She strikes again.
Who do they mean?
It was Nao's mom.
She complains to the school
for just about everything.
You could say that she's
a bit "overprotective."
That's gotta be pretty rough.
Hey, Nao. Are you okay?
[TAKAYUKI] But there's
good news to go with this.
Yup. The bracket
for the summer team
tournament was just decided.
I received the
diagram in the mail
first thing this morning.
Did you really?
Hurry up and show it to us!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Start with that news first!
Well, who do we got?
Spit it out!
Yeah, sure. Give me a sec‐‐
[SHINGO]
Mine now! 'Kay!
Lemme take a look at this thing!
[TAIYO]
Finally! The team tournament!
[ITSUKI]
Who's up first?
It's Hatanooka middle school!
[YUTA] This Joy guy is
a big hit on social media.
It's nuts.
[KANAKO]
Yeah, I guess so. Joy Kusakabe.
He's only half Japanese.
[TOMA]
Just look at him.
[MAKI] He's only in
his second year and‐‐
Wait, he's that tall already?
A matchup like this should
be against the rules.
He's on a whole other level.
It's hard to believe that
he's a second year like us.
We don't know much
about Hatanooka.
What do you think we should do?
You wanna gather
data, don't you?
We have to take a week off
from practice anyway.
Let's try to make use of
that time and form a plan!
A winning strategy!
Hey, you guys?
I might have an idea
that could help you out.
[IZUMI]
Something for Yu to wear.
This one might be
pretty cute on him.
What do you think, Izumi?
Yeah! I think that
would be pretty good.
We can try this one, too!
[YUTA]
Please, um...
[IZUMI, HIKARI]
Hm?
Keep this a secret from Mom.
Sure, No problem.
This'll be our little
secret, promise.
[NAO'S MOM] Aren't you glad
that club is on a break?
Now you have all the
study time you need.
I'll make sure you
take advantage of it.
I know! We can try to get
you into cram school.
I think that would be helpful.
I have a pamphlet for one.
Really? Yeah, sure. That's good.
Think so? Perfect.
Because I already signed
you up for a trial session.
[NAO]
Cool. When?
How's tomorrow?
I can fill out the admission
forms right away.
I'm so glad to see that
you're motivated, Nao.
Uh‐huh.
[RINTARO]
Wait, scouting?
[TAIYO] Yup. At Hatanooka.
But in the past,
outsiders that snooped
at their tennis courts
got reported to the police
if they got caught!
Didn't they make it impossible
to see their players
on the courts by
putting up a new fence
and a buncha shrubbery
in the way?
The shrubs are to keep
perverts out. I'd bet money.
But still. That
doesn't stop them.
There are always a lot of girls
trying to get a glimpse
of that Joy guy.
Those types of fangirls
are the absolute worst.
Stalking his every move
and squealing like harpies.
It's so gross.
Well. Teachers did
try to stop them.
But, they've sorta
given up on it.
They figured that it wasn't
a threat to their security.
It's only a few excited girls.
[TSUBASA] So a group of boys
like us would stand out.
Forget standing out!
They would totally
report us to the police!
Wouldn't it be better to
just be straightforward
with them and say
that we're there
to watch some of the matches?
[RINTARO]
Well, yeah.
But, they'll probably know
we're their opponents,
and it's gonna be pretty obvious
that we're scouting them.
So that wouldn't work.
Yeah, good point.
We really only
have one advantage.
None of the other schools know
anything about what we can do.
Which means, if we wanna
keep the advantage,
we can't reveal ourselves
and risk them scouting us back.
[SHINGO]
Well, if that's the case,
let's just lie about
what school we're from.
No way.
'Kay, "no way" it is.
It'll be fine as long
as we don't get caught.
Hang on. I know.
We can just have her go!
Huh? What? Are you crazy?
Yeah, hard pass.
I think we'd probably
get more info
if a club member went to watch.
We're trying to analyze them.
Learn their plays and practices.
Ya See? I can't do
any of that kinda stuff.
[YUTA] Why don't we disguise
ourselves as girls and go?
As girls?
'Cause...
...there's gonna be lots of
girls watching Joy anyway;
we can blend right in with them.
Huh? You're serious about this?
I never considered it,
but it could work.
Well? Why's everyone so quiet?
Any takers?
Wait! Where are you
gonna get clothes?
And what about your hair?
I have two older sisters,
and we can borrow outfits
and wigs from them.
I can film the match,
and someone should
come with me as backup.
You've thought this through.
Well, it works for me!
But who else here could
pull it off with you?
Yeah? What?
[zipping]
Wow. You know how
to use this makeup?
Yeah, my older sisters
taught me how to do it.
[MAKI]
That makes sense.
Don't you think this
is kinda weird?
Not really.
[YUTA]
Oh? That's how you truly feel?
Well, I get how other
people might think
it's weird, but it
doesn't bother me.
No one should have to fit
into a mold that's not
made for them, so they
should do what they want
to find out who they are.
That make sense?
[YUTA] It does.
To be completely honest,
I'm not really
sure about myself.
There's actually this
friend of my mom's.
Legally, he's
registered as female,
but everything else
about him is male.
Really? How so?
It's referred to
as "FTM," right?
How did you know?
He told me all about it.
A while back.
He and my mom have been friends
since they were
in college together.
And ever since I
was a little kid,
he's been there for me.
Even helped me study.
I really love him.
Always have.
My mom was busy with
work all the time.
So he stepped in when
she couldn't care for me.
And without hesitation.
I always considered him
a part of my family.
That sounds nice.
[MAKI] When he was young,
things didn't really feel right.
He knew pretty early on.
And he told me that while
he was in middle school,
it was painful to wear
the girl's uniform.
But he realized no one
else felt the same way.
He was afraid to talk
to his parents about it,
thinking he was betraying
them or something.
He also didn't want to
disappoint or upset them.
He kept all these
feelings inside.
It was pretty agonizing.
He told me he didn't
feel comfortable
in his own skin, and felt alone.
He was terrified of the
future, until one day,
he got tired of being scared.
After graduating and moving out,
he started living
his life as a man.
When he did, that unease
he felt went away.
And that helped.
It made the pain in his
heart a lot more bearable.
Things were better for him.
And the aching got weaker.
That's good for him.
Honestly, I can't fully relate
to that type of situation,
but I do understand
what it's like to wonder
about the meaning
of life and my place
in the world we live in.
Who I am and what could be
the purpose of my existence.
There's a lot to think about.
[YUTA gasps] Yeah, I get it.
I sorta feel the same way.
If I had to say...
I think I'm non‐binary.
Though, it doesn't feel right
to have to be categorized.
But still...
People always want
some sort of label,
one way or another.
How do I find out what I want?
Or learn about who I really am
and who I wanna become one day?
A lot of people wonder that.
I feel that way, too.
Can't help but think
that I'm pretty
out of place in life sometimes.
"Out of place"?
It's like when you feel
something is wrong,
but you don't know
exactly what it is.
Not knowing how to
justify that feeling
tends to make it worse.
I'm positive that he
must've felt that way.
Is it really that important
that you label yourself
a man or a woman?
Does it matter?
Why do people worry about
that in the first place?
I mean, yeah, there are
people who care about it.
But the only person who
can truly understand
what you feel is you.
Sure, others can try
their best to empathize,
but everyone is unique.
I don't pretend like I
know someone else's pain.
But I think it's good
to have some perspective
and be considerate.
Would you be okay with telling
me that person's name?
It's Shou. That's what
I've always called him.
But he used to go
by the name "Shouko."
I suppose a name like that
can confuse some people
when they look at him, so he
goes by "Shou" for short.
If you ask me, I think that
he's a lot more comfortable
with that just being his name.
Uh‐huh. I feel like
I understand that.
Both of my older sisters
shorten my name down
and just refer to me as "Yu."
And I really like that name.
It suits me perfectly.
[MAKI]
Well. Okay.
Then that's what I'll call
you from now on, Yu.
Sure. Thank you, Maki.
[MAKI chuckles]
[YUTA]
All done.
‐‐[TOMA gasps]
‐‐Oh, wow. That's amazing!
I mean. That's so awesome!
Did you end up bringing
a video camera with you?
Yeah, I borrowed
it from my dad.
You don't think we'll
get found out, do you?
Umm. I guess we'll see.
I have no idea what
to expect here.
[MAKI]
I thought the exact same thing.
[gasps]
[BOTH]
Whoa!
Wow!
[SHINGO]
Oh, dang!
[TAIYO]
No way!
Way to go. You pulled it off!
Sure did! Great work!
[SHINGO] Even when
standing next to Mitsue,
they blend right in.
Would you like to share
your thoughts, Shinjo?
Yeah. I think
we'll be just fine.
‐‐Oh... Ouch!
‐‐[KANAKO] No!
All right, let's go!
Huh? Hey it's Toma. Hi, guys.
‐‐Oh?
‐‐[TOMA] Huh, Takuto?
What're you doing here?
I'm on my way to a
basketball match, that's all!
But forget about me!
Who are those two?
They're just a couple
friends of mine.
You don't know them,
so who cares?
Don't you have a basketball
game to get to?
Better hurry!
[TAKUTO] Aw, come on, how'd
you meet those two cuties?
Just introduce me, wouldja?
[TOMA]
Uh, yeah, no!
They're people we
randomly ran into!
Forget about it!
Relax! I don't get
what the big deal is!
Listen!
Go to your match and lose
it already, would ya?
Dude! What are you
freaking out about?
That was pretty harsh, man.
[GROUPIE 8A]
Hey, Joy!
[GROUPIE 8B]
He's the coolest
[GROUPIE 8A]
Smile!
[GROUPIE 8C]
Look at him go!
[GROUPIE 8A]
Give us a smile!
[GROUPIE 8A] Did you see that?
He actually did it!
He looked at me!
Move it, coming through,
outta the way,
we're watching!
You didn't reserve this spot,
so I can watch wherever I want.
Where'd you come from?
I've never seen you.
‐‐I wouldn't worry about it.
‐‐[GROUPIE 8B] Watch it!
What's her problem?
All right, we can see
him clearly from here.
Yeah, the shot's perfect.
[GROUPIE 8B] You can't just show
up and boss us around like that!
Ah, shut it, you cow.
Huh?
[YUTA]
Joy really is amazing.
Seeing him up close
like this confirms it.
[MAKI]
Yeah.
[JOY]
There!
[MAKI]
I see how it is.
[TSUBASA] Mitsue's
arguing with some girls.
[TAIYO] She's the perfect
distraction at a time like this.
She sure knows how to be
a tricky one, doesn't she?
[NAO] Yeah, people barely
even noticed Maki and Yuta,
so they're able to
scout Joy no problem!
It's still risky.
But Mitsue's putting
herself on the line
to give those two exactly
the kind of cover they need.
Man, she's good.
I'm pretty sure we're older
than you three, am I right?
And why does that
matter, huh?
Brats like you should
respect their elders!
I don't have to respect
a hag like you.
‐‐You little!
‐‐[MAKI] That's enough.
Let's go.
[KANAKO]
Okay.
Later! He's all
yours now, grandma!
Don't you dare come back!
Yeah! Leave!
Or else we'll report you!
Nice work. How'd it go?
Good. And it was all
thanks to Mitsue.
[MAKI]
That looks bad.
[SHINGO] They stomped all
over you. Those jerks.
I can't believe that would
go that far three‐on‐one.
You okay?
Let's clean your shoes.
It'll just take a second.
It's fine. I don't care.
[MAKI]
You did all of that for us,
even though you
were outnumbered.
It must've been scary,
but it's okay now.
You can relax.
Yeah, whatever.
[YUTA] Y'know. I'm still
not sure what I want.
[MAKI]
What do you mean?
To tell you the truth,
I don't think
I've settled on becoming
a girl just yet.
Today was like going out
and walking around
in a girls' school.
And I'm not sure it was for me.
And yet...
I don't really know if I can
keep going on as a boy.
I can't say for sure
if I have it in me.
It's totally fine if
you're unsure right now.
[YUTA] But they say
the normal thing to do
is to make up your
mind and pick one.
Even if that's true,
you don't have to force
yourself to make a decision.
If we live life at our own
pace, there's always time.
Well, when you
put it that way...
You might be right.
[RINTARO] Unbelievable. He's
a total elite. It's insane.
We'll never be
able to beat him,
no matter what we do.
[ITSUKI] But a team tournament
takes a total of three teams.
Even if we lose a match to Joy,
it's fine if we win
our other ones.
Yeah, I know that, but still...
[NAO]
Then forget Joy!
Let's focus on the other pairs!
You'll lose all three matches
with that kinda mentality.
[TAIYO gasps]
That was harsh, don't you think?
[KANAKO] I'm not trying
to be mean about it.
I'm just saying
that's not the right
attitude you should have.
Yeah, good point.
We'll never win if we're
bein' all negative.
We'll have to focus our
efforts on getting better.
We're allowed to resume practice
starting this Saturday.
Let's do a challenge match.
What's a challenge match?
[TAKAYUKI]
Hey, Ms. Murou?
Sounds great, right?
The Soft Tennis Club boys
versus the girls
in a challenge match?
What do ya say?
Will you? Please?
You wanna have a practice
match against us?
I dunno. Didn't we just have one
at the beginning of May?
[TAKAYUKI]
We did, but that was, uh...
Awful, if I had
to put it gently.
[TAKAYUKI]
I definitely think this time
it's gonna be different.
Those boys have really turned
themselves around, I swear!
But what about you?
Have you "turned
yourself around"
like those boys have?
Yes?
Another challenge match, huh?
Why not? The boys' club's
been working hard lately.
[ITSUKI] C'mon, I'm
begging you, sis! Please!
You wanna play us, again?
I mean, I personally don't have
anything against the idea.
That's great!
Could you ask that
Black Butterfly‐‐ Oh.
I mean Captain Takada about it?
I don't mind passing
the message along to her,
but I can't make promises.
The tournament is
coming up soon, so...
Sounds like Namie's
got it tough, too.
[knocking]
Yeah! Come in!
Hello. Aren't you, uh...?
It's Mitsue.
Do you have a minute?
There's something
I wanna ask you.
[TAKAYUKI]
Yes, of course. What's up?
[KANAKO] Don't you think
it's kinda cluttered in here?
Maybe.
Uh...
Could you please look
at some of my drawings?
[gasps]
[TAKAYUKI]
Mm... Mm. Whoa.
[TAKAYUKI] Are you studying
art from somewhere?
[KANAKO] No. My family doesn't
have that kind of money.
My mom keeps telling
me that it's stupid
to draw this kinda stuff.
And that all this manga
is a waste of time.
She keeps saying
that drawing pictures
isn't something
respectable people do.
I'm not surprised
she thinks that way.
Studying is typically more
useful for normal people.
What is "normal" anyway?
And what makes
something "respectable"?
So many things in the world
don't fall under "normal."
And that makes for a lot
that isn't respectable.
[KANAKO]
But all I wanna do is make art.
Is something as
simple as drawing
really that ridiculous
of a passion to have?
Is it just because I'm stupid?
Is that the reason
I like to draw?
But the more I do it,
the more I want to improve.
One day, I wanna
have the ability
to bring the images
I see in my head to life.
So, please!
I wanna learn more and
get better at drawing!
All those boys...
Even though soft tennis
is totally useless to them,
they still push themselves
so hard for it.
At first I just thought
they were dumb.
But then... I realized
that I like to draw,
so I must be dumb, too.
Does that make it
okay for me to push
for what I want and
have dreams of my own?
[sighs]
[MAKI] Huh? Kanako!
Didn't come by today?
[KANAKO] Even I'm not
that bored all the time.
[MAKI]
Are ya hungry right now?
Huh? Why do you ask?
I can tell you're suffering.
You're being really stupid.
Maki is pretty amazing.
What do you mean?
He's got a great sense
for things. Like that.
[MAKI] When you're feeling down,
it helps to eat a buncha food.
Nah, I'll get fat.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess that's just
how he is. Maybe.
[YUTA]
Hey, guys! We got it!
We got the practice match!
We'll be playing
against the girls!
Awesome!
Yeah, that's great!
It's challenge match time!
All right!
Yeah!
For real?
[ITSUKI]
And it's all thanks to you, sis.
Fight on!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Yeah!
[knocking]
Hey, sis? Hello?
[YUTA'S MOM]
What are you doing? Well, Yuta?
I, um...
[gasps] Please tell
me this is a joke.
Uh‐‐ Wait, Mom, this isn't...
You know you're a boy, right?
I already have two daughters.
You're my son. So I can't...
Just hear me out,
Mom. I think I'm‐‐
[YUTA'S MOM]
You are a boy, and that's it.
I did all I could to
give you a normal life.
I didn't raise you
to be like this!