[YUTA] Oh, no. And it's going to
take two full months to heal?
[ITSUKI] Then you'll have to
miss the tournament next month.
I'm sorry, guys.
I let everyone down.
It's not like you got
yourself hurt on purpose.
Don't apologize.
Yeah, nobody's blaming you,
but this does mean we've lost
one of our tournament pairs.
Yeah, that's
a pretty big setback.
Tsubasa and Shingo
had a good shot.
If Tsubasa's not gonna
be able to compete
in the summer tournament,
then I guess we're only eligible
if you sub in Nao and me, right?
That's true.
We need to have three pairs to
enter the tournament as a team.
Guys. Get pumped!
Thank you for the encouragement.
This is us.
It's fine. We're still
entering three pairs.
Only one needs to win.
Good point. We've got
better pairs playing.
Even if we lose, they can
still pull it out in the end.
[MAKI]
Don't think of it like that.
[BOTH gasp]
All of us are
members of this team,
and we're all playing to win.
Yeah. Don't leave
it to your teammates.
You have to try.
[BOTH groan]
Wait a sec.
Wouldn't it be better to pair
Shingo with somebody else?
Even without Tsubasa‐‐he's
still one of the best we've got.
[SHINGO]
Cut the crap!
The whole reason
we've gotten so much better
is because of our partners.
This isn't the time
to mess with that!
If Tsubasa is out of
the tournament, then so am I!
That's what it means
to be partners!
[TSUBASA gasps]
So you and Taiyo
are gonna go in our place,
and you're going to give it
everything you've got!
Have some confidence.
You're better players
than you used to be.
That's right, and I'll be
there cheering you on, too.
I wanna see you do your best!
Understand? I'm counting on you.
[BOTH grunt]
Hey, guys.
Victory dance! Let's go!
Grasshopper time?
I'm in!
Yeah. Get up!
We're doing this!
‐‐Fight!
‐‐[GROUP] Fight!
[ALL]
Whoa...!
[AYA] What? The regional
prelims are coming up?
This Sunday?
It's fine if you can't come.
I'll be okay even if
you're not watching me.
I feel so loved.
But one of the projects I worked
on is being inspected that day,
so I wouldn't be able
to make it out anyway.
Wish I could.
All good.
Go bring home that bread.
Will do.
Ah! I know!
Take this.
That's a lot.
What's the occasion?
You have a match, right?
Why don't you take that
and pick up a new racket?
Yeah, not a good idea,
changing things up
before a match.
Really?
I figured you would play even
better if you had newer stuff.
You're not wrong
about that, but in this case,
it's better for me to have
the equipment I'm used to.
I would need some practice
time to adjust to the feel
of a new racket.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able
to place my shots right.
I see.
There's more to this
game than I thought.
Well, then consider this
a special allowance
for the hard work you've
been putting in lately.
[MAKI] That actually
works out perfectly.
[TOMA]
So. What's this about, anyway?
Sorry?
Is all this for dinner?
No, only some of it.
The rest is for animal feed.
There's this stray
I wanna catch.
You'll see.
[MAKI]
What are you shopping for?
A wristband.
I wanted to pick up a new one
before our next match.
Ah. Gotta keep it fresh, right?
That's not the point.
I don't have time to towel
myself off when I'm playing.
Then it's not
just about looking cool.
Of course not.
What kind of sport
do you think this is?
The soft kind.
You're a dork.
[ARASHI] It's the cream of
the crap from Shijo Minami!
[TOMA]
Oji Arashi?
[ARASHI gulps]
Hey. So, Maki...
Got some of those
Okinawan noodles?
No, I don't.
What? Why not?
Why would you ever
not have noodles?
C'mon! Dude. It's not fair!
You got me hooked and
now they're all gone?!
He's not a noodle shop.
I need those
Okinawan fried noodles.
You have to make me some, Maki!
Okay, I will.
When I feel like it.
Ah! When will that be?
I want 'em bad.
I want 'em right now!
Hey, come on, what's with
the silent treatment?
This guy is
Misaki Academy's ace?
I know, how 'bout we go
back to my place or yours
and make some?
How 'bout I give you the recipe
and you make them yourself.
All my energy goes into
being awesome at tennis,
I don't have enough
left to cook!
Fine then, but not today.
[ARASHI]
♪ Okinawan noodles! ♪
♪ Okinawan noodles, hey! ♪
[MAKI]
Seriously?
[ARASHI] I asked
the housekeeper to make some,
but they didn't even come close.
[TOMA]
You sound obsessed.
‐‐Wait.
‐‐What's wrong?
I know those guys!
[gasps]
Itsuse brothers!
[SORA]
Hmm? Riku.
Good to see you, Arashi.
How are you doing?
You're gonna stay in
the tournament long enough
to play us, right?
It'd suck if you didn't.
Of course! You're the only
ones in the regional prelims
who stand a chance against me!
[BOTH laugh]
Yeah, you would say that.
As expected from
the wolf prince of Misaki.
But it seems as if luck's
not on your side.
You know that your
school isn't very‐‐
I'm still gonna crush you
two in a match eventually!
Not unless you find
a good buddy first, Arashi.
You can't play a
doubles match alone.
Hey. Are you two
from Shijo Minami?
They had a great boys'
team back in the day.
[SORA] Yeah, I've heard
all the stories about
that Shinjo‐Oshimi pair.
Won two national
championships back to back.
Oh well, all
of that's in the past now.
[SORA]
Bye, guys.
I hope we see each other
on the court one of these days.
Okay, who're they?
The Itsuse twins.
Their names are Riku and Sora.
And they were
the top‐ranking pair
at last year's national
championship.
Jeez, it's like they're
two of the same guy.
Arashi.
You know the national champions?
Yeah, 'cause I'm awesome.
Did you forget about that?
Oh well, in any case.
Those two are total beasts.
[RYOMA] I'm looking
forward to your match.
This will be your
first time playing
with Maki for real, right?
That's right. What about it?
Y'know. A while back,
he called and asked me
to show him how
to slice his serves.
I gave him some lessons.
He's good.
He's got a natural feel for
the game and he learns fast.
You two could do pretty well.
That's good to hear.
Do you have anything to
talk about besides him?
Anyway. I'll be at your match.
Have fun with it, bro.
[MAKI]
What d'ya think?
Decent serve, right?
You kidding? That curve is nuts!
Awesome!
[chuckles]
[knocking]
Yes?
Oh, hey. What's up?
[RINTARO'S MOM] Honey, we have
something important to tell you.
Okay. Is it something serious?
Rintaro.
We recently received a message
about your birth mother.
The agency informed
us that your mom
got in touch with them hoping
that she would be able
to set up a meeting with you.
My mother?
[TOMA'S MOM] You're not done?
How am I supposed to clean?
You know why
this happens, right?
Because you eat out
before you come home,
and by dinnertime,
you never have an appetite.
Only 'cause
the food here's lousy.
[gasps]
What did you just say?
You know,
that's the reason why Dad
doesn't eat here either.
He can speak for himself!
What gives you the right
to treat me like this?!
Who do you think
you're talking to?!
I'm talking to you!
My mother!
Who else would it be?!
You know I never wanted
to be your mother, don't you?
[TOMA gasps]
If only Ryoma had
minded his own business.
[TOMA gasps]
Well, screw them.
[TOMA]
C'mon, guys! Like you mean it!
[RINTARO gasps]
Yeah!
[TAIYO]
Right!
Uh‐oh.
Ah.
[MAKI]
Is that the president?
[SHINGO]
Kasuga?
[TSUBASA]
Kinuyo's here!
Good to see you giving it
your all, Toma Shinjo.
[TOMA] You came all the way
out to the tennis courts?
It's part of my duty
to observe our school clubs
and ensure that they're
producing results.
[SHINGO]
Aw, crap.
It looks like our captain
may be a marked man.
Don't say that!
I've heard rumors that your club
turned over a new leaf.
You're finally making
a real effort.
We don't want to get disbanded.
And you won't be,
as long as you can win a single
match at the summer tournament.
That hardly seems like
a high bar to clear, right?
It's disappointing to think
that it's still giving
your club so much trouble.
What exactly have you
been doing until now?
Apart from wasting club funding.
Ah. But perhaps I'm being cruel.
Do you think?
You have nothing
to apologize for.
We're only in this situation
because we haven't taken
the club seriously until now.
We all know that. It's on us.
Thank you for giving us
a chance to do better.
It's been fun.
And please...
...cheer us on.
[KINUYO giggles]
[TAIYO grunts] Kinuyo's smile
always feels like a threat.
I don't think it is.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[YUTA chuckles]
[TAIYO]
How does the bracket look?
[ITSUKI]
Really, really bad.
[RINTARO whimpers]
[NAO]
Come on, why?
[TSUBASA]
Screwed right out of the gate.
[SHINGO]
I know, man.
[YUTA] You guys, don't talk
like we've already lost!
[TOMA]
Seriously. Have we been cursed?
[MAKI groans
Things just got interesting.
[knocking]
[TAKAYUKI]
Come in!
[TOMA]
Pardon me.
[AYA] Aww, why did I
fall back to sleep?
Looks like Maki
already took off.
[KANAKO] Let me through
please! 'Scuse me!
[TAKAYUKI] Looks
like Futsu and Ameno
are gonna be playing first.
You're on court three.
[RINTARO] No worries,
Mr. Sakurai. We've got this.
[ITSUKI] Yeah, no point in
freaking out about it now.
Barely made it!
[RINTARO]
Perfect timing, Kanako.
[ARASHI] Hey, the Shijo Minami
scrub squad's here!
Are the nerves
getting to you yet?
Hey, what are you doing here?
You know. Watching
you guys get spanked.
[SHINGO grunts]
Good answer...
Hold on. Are you sure
you have time for that?
Aren't you playing?
In the first round
of the prelims?
Obviously not, I'm seeded.
Sure is boring having to wait.
[TSUBASA]
Pfft. Smug little jerk.
Right, that kid was
super good, wasn't he?
Even though he seems
like a total goofball?
[TAIYO'S DAD]
Ah. We found him, Mama!
Hi, Taiyo! We came
to cheer you on!
Who's that?
They're Taiyo's parents.
Yeah, they show up
anytime he has a match.
It all makes sense now.
You guys... You didn't
need to come to this one!
But I couldn't just sit at
home and worry all day!
Take it easy.
We wouldn't want you
to get yourself hurt
in the middle of a game.
So we brought this.
‐‐Hold onto it.
‐‐[gasps] Wait...
I'm sure you're nervous
about the match.
But even if you don't win today,
you need to remember that
it's not your fault, okay?
That's right, it takes
two to play soft tennis.
Nothing you can do if you have
to pick up your partner's slack.
[TAIYO'S MOM] Exactly!
So if that other boy
is dragging you down‐‐
Don't say that!
[BOTH gasp]
He's my partner,
and we're both responsible
whether we win or lose!
That's what a pair is!
Of course, sweetie.
I didn't mean‐‐
You're exactly right,
Taiyo, and it makes me
so proud to be your father
that you're mature enough
to think about it like that.
[laughs]
[TAIYO'S MOM]
Yeah, me, too!
[SHINGO] So Rintaro and
Itsuki get to be the ones
to kick things off huh?
Yeah, they're up against a pair
of third years from Johoku.
Is that good or bad?
Johoku Middle School
isn't a championship club,
but they've still got some
pretty decent players,
and this pair has
more experience.
The match won't be easy.
Well, damn.
You guys have the worst luck.
Serving side: Johoku Middle,
Ashitaka and Murai.
Receiving side:
Shijo Minami, Futsu and Ameno.
This will be a five‐game match.
Play ball!
‐‐Sorry, that's on me.
‐‐It's fine.
At least now we know
what their serves are like.
Compared to the Black Butterfly,
these guys are no big deal.
Hah!
[RINTARO]
Hm. Yeah, that's true.
Takada's serves are
on a whole 'nother level.
One‐Zero!
[MURAI gasps]
That's right, Itsuki,
they got nothing on you!
We can win this game!
[chuckles]
[OFFICIAL 10A]
One all!
‐‐Yeah!
‐‐Keep it up, guys!
[MURAI gasps]
‐‐Change sides!
‐‐[SHINGO] Good job!
All right, you guys,
that's one game down!
They're pretty good.
They're making
all the right moves.
Playing confidently.
‐‐[RINTARO] Yeah!
‐‐[TSUBASA] Awesome!
All right,
they're up two‐nothing!
[TAIYO]
Okay. One more!
[NAO]
They might really do it!
I think they've got this,
as long as they can
keep the pace going!
Can they?
You don't think so?
[MAKI] Hm. Well,
I could be wrong, but...
[OFFICIAL 10A]
Game score: Zero‐Two!
[RINTARO panting
[GROUP sighing]
[panting]
Uh‐‐ Oh!
They tied it up.
The final game now.
[NAO]
Am I seeing things,
or are Rintaro's movements
a little bit off?
Yeah. I was noticing that, too.
What's up, Rintaro?
Is your leg cramping?
Of all the times...
This sucks. Why right now?
[sighs] It's okay. Stay in the
middle and go for what you can.
Let me cover
the baseline for you.
Got it.
[grunting]
That's okay,
you're still in it, you two!
Yeah, don't give up!
[RINTARO panting]
[gasps]
Wah‐‐!
[OFFICIAL 10A]
Game and set!
With a score of
three games to two,
the winners are Ashitaka
and Murai of Johoku Middle.
Rintaro's leg was acting up.
Sure seems that way.
Man, that's rough.
It's all part of the game.
[MAKI]
Toma?
Sorry. In the end,
I was just dead weight.
That's not true.
We had those guys on the ropes.
Nine times out of ten,
we win that match.
[TSUBASA]
Good work, guys!
[TOMA]
That was an awesome match!
‐‐[MAKI] You gave 'em a fight!
‐‐[TOMA] No worries!
[TAIYO whimpers]
They look like they're
about to be executed.
C'mon, guys!
This is the time to smile!
You'll look cooler!
You think so?
[chuckles nervously]
Not so much.
[MAKI] Arashi. This
Sasaki‐Kawakami pair.
They're third years
at Misaki Academy.
Do you know 'em?
Lessee, seems those
names do ring a bell.
What's up? Are you playing
them in the tournament?
Something like that.
[ARASHI]
Whoa! Are those for me?!
Ahh...
Oh, yeah!
This is the best food ever made!
Now where were we?
Your teammates?
Yeah, they're pretty good.
Not as good as me,
but prob'ly better than you.
Obviously. So.
What about their playstyle?
I guess you'd
call 'em a textbook pair.
Orthodox strategy
with great execution.
They try to get
a long rally going,
make you chase their
shots all over the place,
and mess up your positioning.
Once you leave 'em an opening,
Kawakami blasts one
through from midcourt.
In other words,
they're boring.
Right.
‐‐Animal feed. Got it.
‐‐So good!
So. Let's see...
We're screwed, right?
We're playing
third years from Misaki.
Looking at it realistically,
we don't have a
chance at winning.
In the end, it's gonna come down
to Toma and Maki, I guess.
[growls]
I thought I told you
to cut the crap!
If you go in
thinking that you'll lose,
you're always gonna be right!
You guys pushed yourselves
harder than anyone else.
Did you really bust your asses
for two and a half months
just to give up once it was
time to play a real match?
[TAIYO, NAO sigh]
[MAKI] This is what
you've been working for.
Try to have some fun.
I'd say your
chances are 50‐50.
I'm not sure our odds
are that good.
You're giving us way
too much credit, guys.
More like you're not
giving yourself enough.
What you really
need is confidence.
You're playing against
humans just like you,
and humans mess up.
Don't they? And they
mess up even more
when you hit 'em with something
that they don't expect.
Something they don't expect?
What, like that trick
play we tried out before?
We were just doing
that as a joke, weren't we?
I thought so.
[MAKI] Sure, but these
guys don't know that.
[BOTH gasp]
Ah! They're starting!
Do your best, Taiyo!
[OFFICIAL 10B] Serving side:
Shijo Minami Middle.
Ishigami and Tsukinose.
Receiving side: Misaki Academy.
Sasaki and Kawakami.
It's a five‐game match.
Play ball!
‐‐Hell yeah!
‐‐That was great, Nao!
So, you think they're
just gonna have the guy
in back charge the net?
The whole match? There's no way.
For real?
Shit!
Awesome!
That running strategy
they came up with is working!
Yeah, not bad.
[TOMA] But can they keep
doing it for a whole set?
Which one was
playing front again?
I honestly have no idea anymore.
[TAIYO]
Keep moving. Keep moving!
[NAO]
Run. Don't stop!
I'm impressed that they
can keep running so long.
It looks like all
the running they do
during practice
is paying off now.
Those two made it work.
Almost there!
You can do it, guys!
We're at the final game.
It's turned into
an endurance match.
The game score is two all.
Final game!
We've gotten
this far with this strategy.
[OFFICIAL 10B]
Fault!
That's okay!
[OFFICIAL 10B]
Double fault!
Come on, we're so close!
Don't give up!
[RINTARO]
Keep it up, you're still in it!
You're almost there!
They're done. Out of gas.
[OFFICIAL 10B] The match goes to
Sasaki and Kawakami from Misaki,
with a game score
of three to two.
[CROWD cheering]
You guys really get around.
It was hard to keep up.
Look at our Taiyo!
He did so good!
Great work!
[SHINGO]
I'm proud of you!
You were awesome out there!
You took Misaki to
a final game. Good job!
[TSUBASA] Now go get changed,
'cause you're soaked...
I knew it would
come to this in the end.
[MAKI]
We're up next. You ready to go?
It's down to us.
We have to win this.
Yep. Seems that way.
‐‐[GIRLS squealing]
‐‐[OFFICIAL 10C] Playing next.
Ootomo and Kusakabe
from Hatanooka Middle.
versus Shinjo and Katsuragi
from Shijo Minami Middle.
Good luck.
You, too.
[MAKI] Now that I'm standing
face to face with him,
this guy is huge!