Shinjo. You can do it.
I don't think that's gonna
do anything for them.
Maybe, but I really want
them to win this match.
They've all been working
so hard to get better.
You'd have to be
a fool to believe
that working hard is
the way to get ahead.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Game score, 0‐2!
I'm still not sure
about this plan.
Here goes nothing!
[grunts]
At least you can aim!
[BOTH grunt]
‐‐They're on the board!
‐‐[TSUBASA] Awesome!
Luck was on our side.
Do not get in my way again.
[SHINJIRO]
Right, sorry.
[MAKI]
Hm?
[grunts]
Where's my gap? Come on.
[TOMA]
There it is!
[gasps]
This one's mine!
My bad.
Shut up.
Hey, nice smash.
Think we can keep this going?
Oh, yeah.
[MAKI]
With these guys,
Oji is gonna try to control
every play they make.
He doesn't think of Sunaga
as an equal on the court.
He's just an accessory.
Which means Oji doesn't
really have a teammate.
Just spare parts.
Sunaga barely gets a
chance to act because
Oji's strategy doesn't allow
him to make decisions.
Maybe. But the stronger player
should take the lead,
right? It makes sense.
Right, and that is what
Oji should be doing.
But instead, he's controlling.
It's different.
And since they're not
really playing as partners,
they lose their
strength as a pair.
I think I get it.
[MAKI] These guys' biggest
weakness as a pair
is that they're not one.
And we can use that.
Here's the plan.
Aim the ball directly
between them
anytime you see an opening.
I know it'll work.
We can win if we throw
Oji off his rhythm.
[MAKI] Though, if this
was singles, I don't think
any of us would stand a chance.
[yells]
[grunts]
[ARASHI yells]
You need a partner
in a doubles match.
This is nuts.
Damn you!
[BOTH grunt]
Uh. That's game. Change sides!
[TAIYO]
Way to go, you two!
This is really
happening, isn't it?
You're doing amazing!
Yeah. Keep it up!
They've won one game
like everybody else.
You all need to chill.
We're doing fine.
Once your eyes adjust to it,
Oji's serve isn't hard to hit.
After that, we just have
to follow the plan.
We can win.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Game score, 2‐1!
Time to burn this trash.
First fault!
I screwed up the toss.
Ah, crap!
Double fault!
Oh, crap, he's pissed.
0‐2!
[grunts]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Fault!
[TOMA grunts]
[ARASHI grunts]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Double fault!
[ALL cheering]
That's two friggin' games!
Wow, they actually tied it up!
They might really win.
Final time!
No way I could have called this.
What does he mean
"final time," huh?
Huh? Right. Each pair has
won two games out of five,
so the match will go to whoever
can take this next one.
When they play a full set,
there's a different
scoring system used
just for the final game.
For most of the set, it takes
four points to win a game.
But in the last game,
they play to seven.
Why bother making
it all so complicated?
[KADOWAKI sighs] It looks
like our star pair's biggest
weakness is coming
back to bite them.
I think that's
what my boys want.
In fact, they may have built
their whole strategy around it.
Uh! Well, in that case,
I think Oji's about
to have a bad time.
[ARASHI]
What a joke.
How did these nobodies
take me to a final game?
That doesn't happen!
The game score is two all.
Final game!
[grunts]
[TOMA]
So fast!
[TOMA grunts]
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Advantage in!
You can do this, Shinjo.
Did he just say "advantage"?
Then we lose if we
give up another point?
They'll be fine.
I know they will!
How about this?
[MAKI]
I see it!
[MISAKI CROWD gasps]
He got it!
They caught up!
[ALL cheer]
This is crazy.
They're at deuce!
With Arashi.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Deuce!
How am I at deuce?
Who do these guys
think they are?
We've come so far.
I want to win. I have to!
[MAKI grunts]
They're pulling these
shots outta nowhere.
Jeez, they're good.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Advantage out!
We won't lose here. No way!
Gotcha!
[ALL cheer]
We're still in this thing.
I'm havin' way too much
fun to let it end here.
Huh?
I love this. For real.
Heh.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Deuce again!
[panting]
How are they giving me
so much trouble?
I don't get it!
That visor kid has no idea
what the hell he's doing!
[MAKI grunts]
I'm not gonna lose
to you scrubs!
Arashi...
[TOMA grunts]
Ah, shit. I thought we
had him with that one!
Ugh. This match is
making my stomach hurt.
It's okay.
I know that they'll
catch up again!
Uh?
Good shot, Sunaga.
Yeah, thanks Oji.
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Advantage in!
[grunts]
[TOMA grunts]
[ALL cheer]
[panting]
I see how it is. Sunaga.
Yeah?
I'm sorry for before.
Go for anything you
think you can get.
Help me out.
Uh. Yeah. Sure thing.
Let's do this.
Deuce. Play ball!
This is their third
time at advantage.
But our guys are still
hanging in there.
It'll be okay!
They caught on and
started working as a team.
I was hoping that
we could finish this
before they figured it out.
[gasps]
Shit!
Nice volley!
Yeah, we're back to deuce!
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Change sides!
So. When exactly is this whole
deuce thing gonna end?
There has to be a
two‐point difference,
so someone needs to win
consecutive points.
But then what happens
if they just keep
trading points back
and forth like this?
They stay at deuce forever?
Technically, that's
what the rules say.
Are these guys ever
gonna get to go home?
Still deuce. Play ball!
I'm ending this
right now. Let's go!
[gasps]
Jeez. You mean he
can still pull off
a serve like that?
Even after running
around the court
like a madman the whole set!
This guy's got our number.
He's got better technique
and he has more stamina.
Yeah. Arashi's a real athlete.
I forgot all about the basics.
Did he make me do that?
[MISAKI OFFICIAL 6D]
Advantage in!
Can I end it?
Is he going left or right?
Oh, crap!
[yells]
I've got this, okay!
Uh! Yeah. Understood!
[gasps]
No way!
Guys, that was the match.
[ALL cheer]
Ugh. Dammit, that was close!
Shit, why couldn't
you have stayed
on their side, you stupid ball?
The skill gap was too wide.
Doesn't seem that way
to me. Look at them.
This sucks so bad!
After all that.
It ends like this?!
Those two put up
a real fight against
one of the best pairs
in the country!
Yeah, you're right.
Toma and Maki are amazing!
We couldn't make it happen.
No, but it was awesome.
We lost, though.
Well, yeah, but it
was an amazing game.
I had fun!
[gasps]
[ALL laughing]
[KANAKO]
Mm...
What's the matter, Mitsue?
I came to watch these
guys get dunked on.
My day is ruined.
[TSUBASA]
Stop holdin' out on us, Maki!
We need more ideas for training!
[RINTARO]
Before we do any more teamplay
or technique stuff, I think we
all need to work on cardio.
[TAIYO]
Yeah, I agree.
Should help us move
around the court better.
[NAO] It'll be easier
to win if we're able
to outlast our opponents.
That's true.
Wanna take some extra
time on our run?
Sounds good.
Yo, Tsubasa, rack time!
Yeah! Ooh, it hurts so good!
Hell yeah!
Hey, Itsuki.
Yo.
Itsuki?
Are you okay?
Itsuki.
I thought of an
awesome new trick
play for everybody to try out.
Y'wanna work on it today?
[ITSUKI] Uh, yeah?
Sounds awesome. Let's do it!
[NAO]
I see.
That's another thing we're
gonna have to work on.
[TSUBASA]
So we purposely leave one side
open to bait the opponent
into aiming there?
[SHINGO] We have to be fast to
make it work, so let's sprint!
[TSUBASA] But we also need
to have the endurance
to keep playing after.
Right. These are good
things to keep in mind.
Let's put our heads together
and make a schedule.
[TOMA] Good idea.
What do you think, Maki?
Yeah, it's important that we get
the schedule right and all.
Spit it out.
What's on your mind?
[ALL]
Hm?
I don't know.
I'm not sure if pushing
ourselves into more
and more practice is the
right approach to take.
You're saying practicing
isn't the best way
for us to get better?
[TAKAYUKI]
You guys are looking lively!
So is this a strategy meeting?
It's really good to see
you all working so hard.
But don't overdo it, okay?
[TSUBASA] Get real, Tacky!
We can't slow down now.
We still suck real bad
and we're not gonna get
any better unless
we keep practicing!
Right, and we don't
have much time
before the summer tournament!
Hey. Why don't you set us up
another practice match?
Yeah, I think that's
a great idea!
Could you? That'd be awesome!
I'm glad you're excited;
it's great to see
all this enthusiasm.
Which is why you're getting
us another practice match!
Thing is, that positive
attitude won't be enough
to keep up this pace
all the way to summer.
Be careful, or you're
gonna run out of gas.
Shut up, no we won't!
You will.
I'm your club advisor,
so I'm advising you, okay?
If there's one thing I can
offer, it's life experience.
Well, what should we
be doing instead then?
Get away from
school for a while.
Go someplace you can relax.
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Huh?
Sorry, I don't think
I'm following you.
Ba‐da‐da‐da‐da‐da‐da‐
da‐da‐da‐da‐da‐da,
bip, boom, pow!
[KANAKO]
U‐Uh...
Soft Tennis Club members,
you're cordially invited
to a barbecue lunch at the park
by the Tama River this Sunday!
Ha, ha!
‐‐[TAKAYUKI] You mind?
‐‐[TSUBASA] Ah. Charcoal.
[SHINGO] Who woulda thought
Tacky was the outdoorsy type?
[TSUBASA]
Yeah, I'm kinda shocked.
You're kidding, right?
I borrowed all this
stuff from Ms. Murou.
Ah. I wouldn't have
figured that either.
So anyway, whatcha got
in the cooler there?
Oh, just this here.
Think fast!
Whoa, that's a lot
of meat. Oh, man!
Dang, Tacky, you are
not messin' around!
There's game meat, too.
I talked with a friend
of mine and had him send me
some venison and
wild boar to cook.
[MAKI] There are so many
tents out here already.
‐‐[TOMA] Which one's us?
‐‐[YUTA] Ah. I think I see ours.
They're already
setting up the grill.
[KANAKO]
You're late!
[YUTA]
Mitsue?
Morning!
[KANAKO]
Hmph.
Wonder why Mitsue
decided to come.
Doesn't matter. Right, Yuta?
[MAKI]
We brought some pre‐cut veggies.
[SHINGO]
Cool.
[MAKI]
Yuta lent me a hand with those.
[ITSUKI] You're like a pro
on that grill, Makimaki.
[SHINGO]
Look at that!
It's no big trick, I've just
had a lot of practice.
Time to start the yakisoba.
Bring the noodles please.
Got it!
[TOMA]
I brought the water.
[MAKI]
Pour it in the pot to boil.
[TOMA]
Uh, sure thing.
[ARASHI]
All right, Kamuy. Keep it up!
Wait!
Ow.
Hey, I know them!
What's going on?
Man, I love meat!
Do you have any idea what
you're eating right now?
I know it's meat!
[ITSUKI]
Looks great.
[TAIYO]
Everything tastes amazing.
Eat up. We've got tons
of food here, guys.
Oh, man! Who knew
deer was this good?
But I think I might like
the boar even better!
Which makes sense
since it's pork.
Wow, Mitsue. You
sure can eat a lot.
Yeah, what about it?
It's nothing, just...
when I see you at lunch.
You never look like
you enjoy eating.
So what? That's my
business, not yours.
She can't help it.
This food is way too good.
I'm pretty sure all girls
actually eat like crazy.
Like Namie has five meals a day.
I've got two big sisters
and they both eat a ton.
Yeah, so it's normal. Eat up.
Ugh. Gee, thanks. This
isn't awkward or anything.
[KAMUY barks]
Huh?
Yo. Thought I'd come
crash your party.
How's it goin', Arashi?
Taking the dog for a walk?
That's right, this
guy's name is Kamuy.
What a good boy!
Can I?
Sure.
Ready? Now catch!
Thanks for sharing.
You thank him, too, boy.
[barks]
He's as smart as
he is handsome.
[ARASHI]
Obviously, he takes after me.
Hold on. What's the deal?
Is that the angry kid
from the other day?
Why'd he have to show up?
Trying to pick a
fight or something?
Pretty ballsy to come
here alone, if that's it.
Nobody's looking
for a fight, guys!
So, Maki.
From what I hear, you're
still new to soft tennis.
That's right.
It's been, I think
about a month now?
That's it? A month?
Yep. That's it.
Now I'm mad.
Coach put me up against
a total newbie.
But it was still a pretty
good match, wasn't it?
Yeah, one of the best
I've had in a while.
No kidding.
Hey, thanks. Have some barbecue.
We really don't mind sharing,
as long as you don't mind
helpin' us make more.
[ARASHI, SHINGO laughing]
[SHINGO]
Those serves were sick though!
How did you get so good at that?
[ARASHI]
That was 100 percent raw talent.
[SHINGO]
Don't lie.
I bet you do like
1,000 practice swings.
No way. Twice that at least.
[BOTH laugh]
What's up with these two?
They synced up quick because
they each have half a brain.
Whoa. Hey, Maki.
What is this stuff?
It looks like yakisoba.
Yeah. They're Okinawan
fried noodles.
Okinawan fried noodles?
Never had 'em.
Oh, man. This stuff's awesome!
That's good! Okinawan
fried noodles are the best!
There's more!
So, uh. That was
for everybody?
[ARASHI] Sorry. I can't
help myself, guys!
You know?
Is it all gone?
Sure is. But we can make more.
[ARASHI] Whoa, Maki!
You're a beast on that grill!
I'm just cooking lunch, man,
it's really not a big
deal. There we go.
[ARASHI]
That's so cool!
For real, you make
our housekeeper
and our nutritionist
look like amateurs!
Back up. "Housekeeper?"
"Nutritionist?"
That is what he said.
The Prince of Soft Tennis
here must be loaded.
I mean, even his dog
looks expensive.
Aw! Hi there!
Hey, looks like Kamuy has
taken a liking to you, too!
‐‐Who's a good boy?
‐‐[SHINGO] Aw, dude. Jealous.
Arashi! I wanna pet him, too!
[ARASHI]
Sure, that's fine.
As long as Kamuy's okay with it.
[TSUBASA]
Dogs are the best.
[KANAKO] Ugh. Have you dorks
never seen a dog before?
You okay?
Yeah, why?
Sorry. I was wondering why
you're eating by yourself.
Oh. It's fine.
Is there something wrong?
No, I'm good. It's just that...
I have a hard time
being around people
who're having fun.
[YUTA]
Mm... Uh.
[TOMA]
I feel like I'll just mess it up
if I try to take part.
I can't see how I fit in.
I think... I might
be a little broken.
[gasps]
I wanted to ask, Maki.
How did you get your
reflexes so sharp?
What sports did you play before?
We asked him the same
thing when he joined
and he told us he'd never
played a sport in his life.
I guess... Yeah,
that's probably it.
All those chocolate‐
covered critters.
Huh? What chocolate‐
covered critters?
Cockroaches.
[GROUP gasps]
Oh, gross!
[MAKI] Our crappy old
apartment was swarming
with the things. Mom
offered me ten yen apiece
for each one I could catch,
so I got really good at it.
And I think it ended up
training my reflexes
and dynamic vision.
Roach training?
No thanks.
I tried a few things
and found the best way
to catch them was
with chopsticks.
You guys should give
it a shot sometime.
‐‐[GROUP] Ugh...
‐‐[MAKI laughs]
[TAKAYUKI]
Okay then!
So, now that everyone's
full to bursting,
I think it's time that
we all do a team cheer
for victory at
the summer tourn‐‐
[RINTARO]
Hey. Let's do the victory jump
like we did before, guys!
Yeah, good idea!
Man, thinking about
it gets me pumped!
Right, let's do it!
I'm in!
Kinda weird to do
in public, but...
Meh, screw it.
Yeah! I don't know what
we're doin', but I'm in!
You kind of don't go
to our school, dude.
Yeah, so what?
Don't sweat the details!
Hey! Captain!
Yeah. Sorry!
Here we go, guys!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB, ARASHI]
Yeah!
We're gonna win the whole
summer tournament, right? Fight!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB, ARASHI]
Whoa! Fight!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Whoa!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
[HEAD OF YEAR] Sir, how exactly
should we handle this?
[PRINCIPAL] This was about
the Soft Tennis Club?
The boys, you said.
[HEAD OF YEAR] It would seem
they're using outdated,
dangerous training methods.
[PRINCIPAL] And that was a
complaint from a parent, yes?
[HEAD OF YEAR]
Yes, sir.
Apparently, the club
members were forced
to participate in a
Sunday practice yesterday.
[PRINCIPAL grumbles]
This is troublesome.
[HEAD OF YEAR sighs]