[MAKI]
I'm fine from here.
[TOMA] I don't mind
carrying it up for you.
This is part of
the deal we made.
Well, if you insist. Thanks.
What about you guys?
Uh...
[pans scraping]
Do you need help?
[MAKI]
Nah, you'd be in the way.
They had meat on sale today,
so there's plenty
if you want some.
This food... looks great.
It is.
There's no way anyone's
eating this well at my place.
Jealous.
Thanks, Maki.
That's good!
Sorry if I was cranky‐‐
I wanted to be eating
and not cooking.
[TOMA] If you would
let me do the shopping‐‐
No, it's fine.
Hey, neighbor girl.
Why are you still here?
I live one floor
down. Who cares?
So good.
Uh. Hey, Toma.
Why is there one
player up by the net
and one at the back?
[TOMA]
Strategy.
[TOMA] Since there are
two players on a team,
it makes sense for
each one to cover
a different part of the court.
That's the nice thing
about playing as a pair.
But why split the court
into front and back?
One player reads the
game from the baseline
and calls the shots,
and the other looks
for openings to strike.
I get it.
The player combination
must be important.
C'mon. It's just a
system made for people
who aren't good enough
to cut it alone.
That's kinda mean.
I'm back, Maki.
I got off work early!
Huh. Hey, honey,
did you bring guests?
[MAKI]
Hi, Mom. I made us dinner.
There's plenty for everyone.
Oh, gosh, it looks so good!
Hi, everyone. I'm Maki's mother.
I'm Toma Shinjo.
Yuta Asuka. Nice to meet you.
Hi, ma'am. I stayed for dinner.
And Kanako's here, too!
Thank you so much
for getting along
with my son, everybody.
They're not my babysitters.
[AYA]
That's neat.
So you and Toma were
in the same class
until your first year
of elementary school?
I went to a different
school than you guys.
Me, too.
Thanks for having us.
We should get going.
Okay. Stay safe heading home.
And you can come back anytime.
Yes, ma'am.
[TOMA] The games in soft tennis
are played to four points,
then there are multiple
games in a set.
Three, five, seven.
It's always an odd
number, so no ties.
And the matches we play
are usually a single set.
If it's a three‐game
set, the team
has to take two games,
and then they win the match.
Meaning, you can lose one
game and still win overall.
[SHINGO]
Let's go, Taiyo!
Ow, ow, ow! Cut it out,
Shingo, that hurts!
[TSUBASA]
You're like children.
[SHINGO]
Stretch!
[TSUBASA]
Watch your feet!
It's too cramped in
here for that crap!
Hold up. Is Ameno
not here today?
He is. But he'll
be joining us later.
Uh. Is he busy?
Yeah, kinda.
A practice match? All of us?
Maki needs to learn the rules
and pick up the
basics in a hurry.
A match is the fastest way.
Yeah, I get that.
But still, isn't it a little
soon to have him playing games?
[YUTA] I think Katsuragi
will do all right.
He seems like a
fast learner. Look.
You play the net, and
I'll play the baseline.
Sure, sounds good.
But before we do anything,
you need to get that
shirt tucked in.
Why?
Because this is a sport
and there are rules.
[MAKI]
Hm.
He's gonna play a match?
[KANAKO sighs]
[RINTARO]
Serving first:
Toma Shinjo and Maki Katsuragi.
Returning: Taiyo Ishigami
and Shingo Takenouchi.
[SHINGO] Return the first
serve to his feet, okay?
[TAIYO]
Seriously?
[SHINGO] Yeah, give it
straight back to him
with all you've got!
It's a three‐game
match! Play ball!
[TOMA grunts]
[TAIYO]
Right in front of Katsuragi.
[gasps] Huh?
[grunts]
[gasps]
Whoa.
Nice, volley.
Volley? Is that
what that's called?
It is. Keep it up.
Now that's sad.
They gave up an easy
point to a first‐timer.
Good start, you two.
Playin' real smart.
If that's how it is...!
[TOMA grunts]
[yells]
What?
You moron.
[MAKI]
Hey.
I get to serve next, right?
Yeah, that's right.
[MAKI] So I'm supposed to start
off with a hard serve, huh?
[gasps]
No way.
[sighs] That felt good.
Nice serve.
3‐0.
[MAKI grunts]
[RINTARO]
Fault!
Be careful on the next one.
Got it. Let's see. Like that?
[SHINGO]
Take this!
[yells]
[SHINGO]
Wait‐‐
[gasps]
That's game!
Taiyo. You shoulda had that!
Yeah, my bad.
Shingo. How could he get to it?
Change sides!
This is his first time? Really?
He's got sharp eyes.
That's all it is.
Good job.
2‐0!
If they keep screwing
up like that,
it's gonna start
going to his head.
And it's worse with
a guy like him.
[TAIYO yelps]
Game and set! That's 2‐0.
Shinjo and Katsuragi
win the match!
Nice one!
Hold on. It's over?
Did he just win?
[MAKI]
Was that a good start?
[TOMA] Yeah. Try to get
up to the net faster
in the next game, okay?
Sure. I'll focus on that.
[grunts] What?
That was pathetic.
Shut up!
[TAIYO]
Shingo, stop it!
[SHINGO]
Huh?
No fighting, guys,
we're still at school!
Idiot.
We hit everything
straight at him.
Isn't that a little bit much?
It's smart to play your
opponent's weaknesses.
[TSUBASA]
Do it. Rush the net.
[grunts]
[sighs] Nice.
Hey, thanks!
This kid's pissin' me off.
Rintaro.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Ready? 0‐1!
[TSUBASA]
Friggin' pest!
Nice volley.
Yeah!
That's another point.
[TAIYO]
Um. Game, set and match.
With a score of
two games to none,
Shinjo and Katsuragi
are the winners.
[panting]
Katsuragi's really
something else.
He won twice?
I feel like my brain
is breaking here.
Someone needs to knock
this guy down a peg.
[yelps]
That's rough.
Itsuki's playing mean.
Uh.
Don't be scared.
It's a soft ball, relax!
It's not gonna kill you!
[RINTARO]
0‐1!
[grunts]
Let's see.
Katsuragi!
[SHINGO] Stay back!
They're still playing.
Ow.
[ITSUKI]
Welcome to the club!
That's gonna swell up
real nice, newbie.
It's turning into
a dodgeball game.
Looks like they're hazing him.
So. How do I deal with this?
The problem is that
you're not committing
to your movements.
When they do that,
fall back to the baseline.
Understood.
You can change your positioning
once the ball is in play.
So you need to be ready
to make adjustments.
That's a lot to think about.
0‐2!
What is this?
He's not gonna stop moving.
C'mon, take it!
Just hold still!
For real?
Good shot.
Heh, thanks.
Eww. My hand's getting wrecked.
What's the deal with him?
He keeps getting better and
better as the match goes on.
Don't praise the enemy, Nao.
What do you mean "enemy"?
Huh?
We're all in the
same club, aren't we?
[RINTARO]
Game and set!
Match goes to
Shinjo and Katsuragi.
Score, two games to zero.
He swept them. I just
can't believe it.
This can't be right.
How is he that good?
Man. You're amazing.
We might have a chance now!
You guys are pathetic.
What have you been
doing this whole time?
Again? You're really
gonna pull this crap‐‐
[TOMA yells]
[ALL gasp]
Maki's completely right.
How are you this bad?
He took straight sets off
you on his first day!
Is being losers fun to you?
Or are you all too
stupid to get better?
That's not fair.
Everybody really is doing
the best they can.
Then their best is garbage
and they're going to be
garbage at everything.
You might as well
lie down and die!
Shinjo.
Screw this. Bye, you
guys. I'm done here.
That was too much.
I didn't know he had such
a bad temper. Scary.
So, what now?
[sighs]
You're home early. No club?
I took off for the day.
Did everyone else
on the team go home
or just you?
What is the matter with you?
Are you ever going to try?
I am trying. So hard.
[RINTARO] This is
basically what we've got.
Notes on everyone's
personalities and playstyles.
Don't worry. I'll
make a clean copy.
[MAKI]
Thanks, Yuta. Hey, VP?
No need for the title.
Rintaro's fine.
Okay, Rintaro.
Who decided how you guys
should be paired up?
We each picked our own partners.
Mister Sakurai signed
off on it, too.
Doubles partners are
supposed to complement
each other's playstyles, right?
These are leaders and lackeys.
That's a little harsh.
But it's true, isn't it?
Do you really think so?
Okay.
I've got it figured out.
Well, more or less.
[RYOMA] Hey, bro. Did practice
finish up early today?
I dunno. Did work?
I dunno either.
We both ditched.
I think I'm finally done.
Club's a waste of time.
I'm the captain and I can't
do anything for them.
They suck because I do.
Stop saying you suck,
Toma. You don't.
That's not what Mom says.
She thinks I'm useless.
Enough of that.
No more sulking,
sit up and listen to me.
Dude, don't pull me
up by my tie! Jeez.
You're fine.
Sometimes parents
and their children
aren't going to get along.
And you can't blame
yourself for that.
I know how tense things can
be between you and Mom.
But it's not your fault.
[RINTARO]
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
‐‐Is the captain coming?
‐‐[RINTARO] Five!
Doubt it.
[ITSUKI]
Do you think he's still angry?
It'd be weirder if he
was over it already.
[TAIYO]
I don't think that's true.
Speaking of. Why isn't
visor boy here right now?
‐‐[KEI] Namie!
‐‐[NAMIE] Got it.
[NAMIE]
Kei, right side!
Why are you watching the girls
instead of practicing?
I felt like it.
[KANAKO] Are you sure you're
not checking someone out?
Bite me.
Kei, net!
[KEI]
On it!
And now I see.
You leaving early again?
[TOMA]
I'm sick of it.
But you still love
the game, don't you?
[SHINGO]
What the hell are we doing here?
[TSUBASA]
Taking a break, obviously.
[ITSUKI]
Our club is getting disbanded.
Our captain has
gotten sick of us.
I just saw him.
He was back in the locker room
getting changed
into his uniform.
Yeah, I don't think anybody's
gonna buy that one, Nao.
Give it up.
[NAKAO] Oh, hey! It's the
worst club in the school.
How sad.
You mean the tennis team
that sucks too much
to play on the tennis courts?
Could there be anything
lamer than that?
How 'bout hanging
around after class,
starting crap for no reason?
Wait, Ameno?
You're actually in
this trash club?
I am. Now get lost.
It's not his fault.
His sister on the girls' team
got all the good genes.
Oh, yeah, she's paired
with that third year
with the dark tan.
And the whole school knows
she's better than you.
What's that like?
[ITSUKI sighs]
Keep talking. Let's
see what happens.
If only Mom and Dad
had kept it together.
Maybe things wouldn't
be like this.
Dang, that's rough!
Their place is a total dump
now that Mommy's gone.
Really. When have you
been to my house, huh?
I haven't, but I'm
looking directly at you.
And it's pretty easy to see it.
[inaudible]
[ALL gasp]
[yelps]
Are you kidding me?
Crap. Taiyo, come help!
Y‐Yeah!
[TSUBASA]
His head's sliced open.
Here. Take this and keep
the pressure on it.
[NAKAO]
It hurts!
Get him to the nurse's office.
[TSUBASA]
Yeah. Shingo?
[SHINGO]
Stand up, you're okay.
[RINTARO]
Itsuki. Hey, you all right?
Oh, yeah. Great.
You can't let guys
like that get to you.
Ya gotta learn to ignore them.
[MAKI]
It's not that easy.
I was getting pissed off, too.
You were watching all that?
My family's the same way.
It's only me and my mom
at our place now.
But still, don't hit
people with your racket.
Those things aren't cheap.
Huh?
No fighting at school.
You know that.
And if you do fight,
don't use a weapon.
I know you don't wanna
seriously injure someone.
Right?
Luckily, the wound wasn't
as bad as it may have looked,
but a big gash on the
head like that bleeds
way more than you would expect.
He had to be scared.
The fight was my fault.
This is all my doing.
Mostly. Of course you are
the one who swung first.
But it was just
as much his fault
for trying to use your family
situation to make fun of you.
Mister Sakurai!
[TAKAYUKI]
He was wrong for that.
A lot of bullies fail to
understand how much pain
their words can cause people.
Now. Want some candy?
The reason Itsuki doesn't
wanna change clothes
with the rest of us...
is 'cause you're here.
But i‐it's got nothing
to do with you personally.
I'm pretty sure he just
doesn't want you to see
the burn scars he has
all over his back.
I had no idea.
Yeah, and they're
pretty gnarly, too.
But barely anybody in the
school knows about 'em.
It's pretty much
only us in the club.
And now you, too, I guess.
[MAKI]
Really?
[TSUBASA] It happened when
he was only about a year old.
At home with his mom.
[ITSUKI crying]
They found her sitting
there in a daze.
And Itsuki was lying next
to her in his crib, screaming.
The neighbors came after
they heard him crying.
They got him to the hospital.
Yeah. But he didn't
get there fast enough
for them to stop the
scars from forming.
It's not that he's
embarrassed by them.
He's not really trying
to hide them from anybody.
But he still doesn't like
explaining where they came from.
Make sense?
Telling someone that his mom
poured boiling water on him.
That has to be tough.
[ITSUKI] Sorry for making
you deal with this.
If I'm being honest,
it felt good to watch.
That guy kinda had it coming.
That's pretty dark for you.
I'm no angel.
Namie?
Hey, I'm out. I'll see ya!
Bye.
[RINTARO]
Hi, Namie!
Bye, Namie!
[NAMIE]
Oh, hey. See ya later!
What's up?
Talked to Mr. Sakurai.
Yeah?
Don't hit people with rackets.
My bad.
Just headbutt him or
something next time, okay?
Sure, got it.
You coming?
Yeah.
[ITSUKI]
It's your turn to make dinner.
[NAMIE]
What do you want?
I can go by the grocery store.
[ITSUKI]
Fried chicken.
[NAMIE] Again? What do you
wanna have with it?
[ITSUKI]
More fried chicken.
[door clicks]
[RYOMA]
Hey, Toma.
What is it?
Maki really wants
to talk to you.
Here, take my phone.
Hey, Maki.
[MAKI] If the Boys' Soft Tennis
Club ends up disbanding,
I don't get paid, right?
[gasps]
[MAKI] That's not
acceptable. You got it?
So I don't wanna
hear anything else
about you quitting.
[MAKI] You're not allowed,
okay? I forbid it.
Don't even think about it.
Not for a second.
I refuse to hear it.
You understand?
You don't get to give up!
[gasps]
[MAKI]
You and me and the rest of them.
We're better together.
So we're staying together.
Yeah, I get it. I'll
see you all tomorrow.
[MAKI]
Good. We'll be waiting. Later.
[TOMA]
Sorry, everyone.
I skipped the last three days,
but I'm back now and
I want to practice.
I'm sorry for everything
I said before.
I hope you can forgive me.
Yeah, we can. I guess.
Dude, shut up.
You've skipped practice
how many times, now?
Have I?
You even forgot skipping.
Oh, yeah? Stretch!
[ITSUKI]
Shingo! No fighting at school.
[SHINGO]
Yeah, look who's talking!
I know.
Wait, that was it?
No clapback?
It's a good thing he
doesn't have his racket.
Why's that?
Don't worry about it;
we'll catch you up later.
[Hey, guys, I've
got some big news.
I figured out why
you all suck so bad!
What?
‐‐[TSUBASA] Katsuragi!
‐‐[RINTARO] What do you mean?
‐‐[TAIYO] Stop saying that!
‐‐[NAO] So tell us.
All of you picked
the wrong partners.
We need to form some new pairs,
and I mean everyone.
New pairs?