[RINTARO panting]
[ITSUKI] What're you
freaking out about, man?
‐‐My mom was here. Somewhere.
‐‐[ITSUKI] What?
[RINTARO]
She came to watch me play.
I still don't get it.
My birth mother
came to watch me.
Whoa, did you see her?
No. I should just forget it.
Uh. So what now?
[RINTARO gasps]
We've gotta watch Toma and Maki.
Their match is starting!
[TAIYO]
The Itsuse brothers.
I can't believe
they're that good.
So this is what a
completely one‐sided
game looks like.
Don't say that!
The match isn't over yet!
It's barely even started,
so quit whining
like a buncha babies.
[NAO]
Yeah. Sorry.
You're right, we
gotta stay positive.
Yeah, exactly!
Remember which pair's
playin' out there!
Those two're pretty damn good.
We have to believe in them!
[SHINGO]
Let's go, let's go, Shinjo!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Let's go, let's go, Toma!
Let's go, let's go, Maki!
[TAKAYUKI]
There's nothing on the line.
But, I guess they can't
help but try their best.
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Let's go, let's go, Maki!
[TOMA] Incredible. So that's
what champions are like.
We haven't been able
to return a single one
of their shots so far.
Is it over?
[MAKI] Come on, it's
too early to give up.
I mean, we've only
played one match.
Do you have any idea
how we can fight back?
Guess we'll see.
[RIKU]
It's getting way too hot today.
I don't wanna wear myself
out during this match.
We better end it quickly.
[TOMA grunts]
‐‐[OFFICIAL 12A] Fault!
‐‐[gasps]
It's fine!
Damn. Maybe I'm too nervous.
[gasps]
[MAKI]
Toma. Try not to get flustered.
You just gotta relax.
And play normally?
Yup. We'll do the usual.
0‐1!
Those two...
Yeah.
[SORA grunts]
Trying to avoid me,
huh? In that case...
[MAKI] Can't let my guard
down for even a moment.
Not surprised.
Don't worry.
No problem. Let's keep it going.
[grunts]
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Out!
And in the blink of
an eye, we're behind.
By two games.
Hey! How's the match?
[TSUBASA] Where the hell did
the two of you run off to?
[RINTARO]
Nowhere.
You gotta be kidding me.
Those twins are one
away from winning?
It hasn't even been
ten minutes! Aw, man.
They're too good.
And in a completely
different league
from our players.
No! That's not true!
As long as they're still
out there, we can't give up!
Even if we make
zero unforced errors,
I don't think we can beat them.
I've only been playing
for three months,
so it's no shock that I'm
not a match for champions.
But still.
I don't want us to
go down that easily.
We've already come this far.
I kinda wanna make it last.
Shall we?
Let's do it.
[RIKU]
This is such a letdown.
[SORA]
He's nothing like Ryoma Shinjo.
[RIKU]
Is this really all he's got?
What a shame.
He's nothing compared
to his older brother.
[SORA]
The cicadas are singing.
Four more serves,
and this'll be over.
They're done.
[SORA] He retreated
back to the baseline.
Ah!
[RIKU] They're actually
getting some solid hits in.
Ah! Hang in there, guys!
They must've gotten
used to the pace.
And now they can keep up!
What is he doing?
Quit playing around.
Wha‐‐?
[MAKI grunts]
[MAKI] I just have to run
as much as I can!
I'm still new to soft tennis,
so I can't do anything fancy.
But that means it
doesn't really matter
which position I play.
We can try to use that
to our advantage
and change up our positioning
during the point.
That might be enough
to surprise them
and throw them off their game,
then we'll take that opening.
[gasps]
[MAKI]
Run!
[TOMA]
They look just like us!
Keep on moving!
What the‐‐?
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheering]
[OFFICIAL 12A]
0‐1!
All right, that's enough.
[grunts]
[RIKU grunts]
[TOMA grunts]
Ah‐‐
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheers]
Another one?
And on his serve, too.
They showed off
some solid teamwork.
Nice volley!
Nice return!
[OFFICIAL 12A]
0‐2!
Now they're really
pissing me off!
That's a let!
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Fault!
Damn it.
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Double fault!
[SPECTATORS gasp]
Oh, yeah, we'll take it!
Nice, we got a free point!
That's so lucky!
[YUTA]
It wasn't luck at all!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Huh?
They earned their respect, and
now the brothers are nervous.
No, they're afraid
that they might lose.
Come on, please. One more.
What the hell is wrong with me?
These guys are nothing!
[SORA]
Crap!
That's game!
Please change sides!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheers]
Aw, yeah!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheering]
Yes! Show those
champs who's boss!
I can't believe it.
They scored one.
Seriously?
But those two aren't
even contenders!
How did they get
so good all of a sudden?
Keep it up, Maki
You got it. We can do this.
[SORA]
That was a fluke.
Idiot. What does he
think he's doing?
[RIKU]
The speed increased again?
Try as hard as you want.
There's no way you amateurs
could play on our level!
[RIKU]
What the‐‐?
Their shots are
getting more powerful!
[SORA]
They're pressuring us now?
Damn it!
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Out!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheers]
[ARASHI] Oh, hey!
Did those punks lose yet?
Shove it.
[chuckles]
[YUTA]
Uh! 'Scuse me!
Oh! They actually
scored points! Wow!
They got another.
Their hits are putting
a lotta pressure
on the Itsuse brothers.
Yeah.
Those returns have been
pretty impressive so far.
If they win this, then it's tied
and they play one more, right?
Yeah, like that'll happen.
Sora, stop playing recklessly.
Excuse me, Riku?
Why don't you try helping
me finish this thing?
Again.
Together.
So close!
Dang!
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Out!
[MAKI]
There!
[SORA]
Dammit! No!
That's game! It's two all!
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheers]
They won. They won that game!
And now they're tied!
Awesome. That's crazy!
I can't believe
this is happening!
Oh, wow! So cool!
Are we sure aren't all dreaming?
Miraculous.
Man. They're doin'
better than expected.
[CICADAS humming]
For real? No way.
We're in final game
and at regional prelims?
The Itsuse brothers
are in a final game?
Against Shijo Minami
of all schools?
I thought their girls' club
was supposed to be the good one.
Just keep on watching!
These guys are really something!
[TOMA]
Almost done.
[MAKI]
Mm‐hm. We should enjoy this.
Yeah, we should.
Hey, Toma. Soft tennis
has been pretty fun.
I agree. We've had
a great time, right?
[RIKU]
This is our domain.
[SORA] They don't stand
a chance. Not at all.
[RIKU] No way. They're
making it their domain.
[applause]
They scored.
Yeah, they're ahead now.
That's a nice return.
How can this be happening?
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Fault!
Double fault! Change server!
The brothers are struggling
under the pressure.
So early on in the
tournament, too.
That's unbelievable.
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Go, go, let's go, go, go, Toma!
Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight, Maki!
Go, go, let's go, go, go, Toma!
Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight, Maki!
Go, go, let's go, go, go, Toma!
Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight, Maki!
They've got the whole crowd
rootin' for 'em now.
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheers]
[SPECTATORS cheering]
This can't be. Why are we‐‐?
Hey, Riku.
Wake up!
[SPECTATORS gasp]
Ouch!
Snap out of it already!
Right.
And now, hit me back.
[BOTH gasp]
What is this?
[SORA] Good thing we
have the same face.
I can tell exactly
how pathetic I am
just by lookin' at you.
Sorry, I got too worked up.
Let's end this.
Sure, you got it.
That's not good.
[gasps]
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB]
Aw!
That was a close one.
Wouldja lookie there?
They calmed themselves down.
[OFFICIAL 12A]
Change sides!
Out!
Ah, come on, man!
Now we're behind again!
Hang in there, Toma!
You've still got this, Maki!
[sighs] What now?
[MAKI]
Hm. We keep on trying our best?
I feel like they're
taking this seriously now.
Good. Because that
means we were able
to make the champions
play for real.
I guess so.
To think that we'd be
able to get this far...
[laughs]
Is it really that funny?
Yeah, kinda.
I'm glad you think so.
[BOTH laughing]
They both started
laughing outta nowhere.
At an intense time like this?
They're having fun.
[YUTA] Mm‐hm. They are.
They're enjoying it together.
[MAKI]
Amazing!
Game and set!
[SPECTATORS murmuring]
Aw...
[OFFICIAL 12A] With a game
score of three to two,
the pair from Shiratori,
Riku Itsuse and
Sora Itsuse, wins.
You're a great pair.
I'm quite impressed.
You gave us some trouble.
We haven't been pushed
that far in a long time.
Maki Katsuragi.
I'll remember you.
Toma Shinjo.
I look forward to having another
match with you someday.
[TOMA]
Thank you very much.
Thank you. We should
do this again.
[SOFT TENNIS CLUB cheering]
[TOMA]
Whoa!
[MAKI]
Take it easy!
Uh, hey, guys! Try not
to get too excited.
Or at least try to
relax at some point.
They do know that
they lost, right?
These idiots.
[TOMA]
Ryoma.
He said he would come and watch.
You know what's next.
Oh, yeah. I can't wait
for the team tournament!
We played pretty good
games today, too.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Ryoma!
You won't believe this!
‐‐At today's match‐‐
‐‐[TOMA'S MOM] Who is this?
Wait, Mom?
[TOMA'S MOM sighs]
Toma. I guess Ryoma
must've left his phone at home.
Yeah, seems like it.
I wanted to tell him
that I finished my match.
Will you pass that on?
[TOMA'S MOM]
He's such a silly boy.
[TOMA]
Mom? Mom, will you listen?
[TOMA'S MOM]
To what?
Well. I actually
won a match today!
At the tennis tournament. I won.
[TOMA'S MOM]
I see. That's good for you.
And even though we lost
in the end, it was fun!
[TOMA'S MOM] As long as you
tried your best, Toma.
Thanks, Mom.
You know, from now on, can we‐‐
[TOMA'S MOM]
I've been trying my best, too.
Huh?
[TOMA'S MOM]
I can finally be honest
with what I think
and how I feel.
I don't have to hold it in.
I don't have to suffer anymore.
What?
[TOMA'S MOM]
I'm getting a divorce.
[TOMA gasps]
[TOMA'S MOM]
From now on,
you'll be living
with your father.
And I'm going to live together
with Ryoma somewhere else.
But why though?
[TOMA'S MOM laughs]
It's because I hate you.
It's such a relief
to finally say it.
I can stop suffering now
that you're out of my life.
Goodbye, Toma.
Toma!
Hey.
Hey, I'm home!
[MAKI]
These are... Are you here, Shou?
At today's match I...
[gasps]
[MAKI]
What the...? That's not good.
Shou?
Maki.
Hey, where's my mom?
[sighs]
[EMPLOYEE 12A]
Welcome. That'll be 300 yen.
[KANAKO sighs]
[thunder]
[sirens blare]
This can't keep happening.
As long as he's still alive...
...we're trapped.
And we'll never be free.
I'm ending this right now.