Scientifically engineered...
Are you serious?!
Hm.
You mean that...
she's artificial...
made by a bunch of guys in lab coats?
More or less.
No way... You're joking!
I can't blame you for not believing. Most wouldn't...
Common sense seems to negate the
possibility from the very start...
However...
We humans aren't always good at knowing
the limits of common sense. Of all people...
I have to imagine you would understand.
I began my investigation by analyzing the
proteins of which Febri's body is composed...
It wasn't long before I realized that
they were not proteins that occur in nature.
Lolly...
Would you like some, Gekota?
For her part, though, she seems unaware
that she's not just an ordinary person,
wandering through the city.
Of course, you can't tell just by looking at her.
Her body functions very similarly
to the way yours or mine does.
Except there is one problem.
Every time her body produces new cells to replace the old,
it involuntarily produces a certain
amount of toxin at the same time, as well.
Toxin?
Yes...
If left alone, it will accumulate in her body...
causing her internal organs to shut down...
and killing her.
You must be wrong...!
She's doing better now...
That's because of her candy.
A component within it neutralizes the toxin.
It is no exaggeration to say that it's those
suckers that are keeping her alive right now.
Without the lollipops, she dies...
is that what you're trying to tell me?
I'm telling you what I know.
Unfortunately, I can't fill in the details for you...
This could be a mistake made in the
lab or something deliberately built in.
But, either way...
If you want to find out how to keep
her body functioning as it should...
The best idea...
is to track down the people who
created her in the first place.
Who is that...?
Who are the people that created Febri?
And for what reason?!
Are the people who run this city
starting up another twisted experiment?!
I don't know whether this will help or not,
but a number of years ago, I heard some
rumors about a group that was looking into
scientifically recreating human life...
but the rumors evaporated, and I
can't say for sure what happened next.
So... she's a product of that research.
At the time, those sorts of experiments
were the province of the city's underworld.
Meaning?
There are some organizations in
the city that aren't above board.
They exist in the shadows, and are so
powerful that not even Antiskill can touch them.
In case you haven't noticed, I work for the underworld.
Do you think this kind of child's play will get
you anywhere against the underworld of Academy City?
I assume you want to save the girl.
But if you do...
You had better be prepared to face
the darkness at the heart of this city.
Tell me. Is that something you think you're ready for?
Ge-ge-geko! My name is Gekota!
Oh, good. You're back...
What'd the doctor have to say?
Oh...
He says that there's nothing more to
worry about, and we can all get out of here.
Did he really?
Aw, that's wonderful!
So, are you ready to go home?
With you, Ruiko?
Yep...! And Uiharu.
Mm-Hmm!
Do we really think it's safe to go back to my dorm?
There could be another attack couldn't there?
That's a good point...
I'll get in touch with Antiskill.
I'm sure they can step up some patrols.
Yeah... good idea.
That is a long time to spend in a hospital!
Are you hungry?
What would you like for breakfast?
A hamburger!
You've got a new favorite, don't you?
Sounds like it.
Out with it...
I know something's bothering you.
Uh, what?
You've looked pale ever since you
got back from talking to the doctor...
Something got to you. Something he said.
Uh, You... think I look pale?
A cat?
I wonder what it's doing here.
What's up?
Oh, uh... well... I... um...
I forgot to ask the doctor something,
so I'm going to head back there.
You guys go on ahead. I'll catch up, okay?
Now what are you hiding, sissy?
It's been a while since we've seen each other...
Is it okay for you to be out and about?
"I got permission from the doctor to go
out alone, so it shouldn't be a problem,"
Misaka says, providing explanation.
Oh, you did?
Well, that's good, then.
I spoke to that girl who came into
the hospital with you last night.
Huh? Are you talking about...
You mean Febri?
Yes.
I could not help but notice that you stayed up all
night, waiting to see the outcome of her treatment.
"She must be quite important to you..."
You haven't even visited your younger sister lately...
Hey, hold on...
and yet you waited for hours out of
concern "for this young girl... Right?"
Misaka asks with a pouty look and
a dejected slump of her shoulders.
You stop that right now...
It's not like she's more important to me or...
May I continue, please?
Late last night I had a look inside her room.
You have regained consciousness, I see.
Mikoto?
"Not her... Her younger sister...
Or, more precisely, a cellular clone
synthetically created from her DNA map,"
says Misaka, politely introducing herself.
Oh, wow, really...?
Mikoto is your older sister?
Yes.
She is troublesome at times, but still...
Do you want to know something?
I have an older sister, too...
I'd like to see her.
She... has a sister?
If Febri was artificially created...
what does that mean?
Could her sister have been made in a laboratory, too?
"That is not all..."
Something else stood out when I was talking to the girl...
"See..." Misaka pauses for effect...
I sensed that all the knowledge she
possesses seems to adhere to a specific pattern,
one embedded at the most basic level.
Uh... What does that mean?
"It is something that Misaka has experienced.
Similar to the initial stage of
the Testament learning process,"
Misaka reports, observing a comparison.
"In Misaka's opinion..."
It is not unlikely that she received her knowledge
through the use of Testament...
In fact, considering all the
similarities in the underlying pattern,
it is highly probable that the Testament program
developed for the girl... was created by the
same individual who developed Misaka's program...
Says Misaka, expressing her conjecture.
Which would mean...
that she's involved...
I haven't seen her since it started.
Could she really have something to do with Febri?
Did she get involved with another screwed-up project?
I thought...
She was nice.
That other girl...
She showed Misaka what milk tea tasted like.
Huh?
"If it was possible, I would like to see her again...
to express gratitude... but...
That may never happen," Misaka says, resigned.
She may or may not be involved.
Right now I have to focus on the information I do have...
According to what Kongo said...
the people behind the robot attack were upset
because they had failed to "retrieve" Febri.
"Retrieve" implies getting her back.
Does that mean Febri could have
run away from them at some point?
Whatever the case, the best way to obtain more information
is to find out who these people
are and ask them some questions.
And if it turns out that the
underworld really is involved...
Then I can't drag Kuroko...
or any of the others into this.
I'll do it... alone.
Hello...?
Yeah...
Hey, Kongo. What's going on?
What's going on, you ask?
I've been on pins and needles about Febri
ever since I left you yesterday...
When I called the hospital
they said she'd been discharged.
Oh...
Right, sorry...
Mmm... She's fine now.
By the time we left, she'd even gotten her appetite back,
so there should be no cause for concern.
Well, that's terrific news!
I'll pass that message along to Awatsuki and Wannai.
Yeah... Please do.
Uh...
I actually feel pretty awful...
I'm afraid in all the confusion,
I might have hurt their feelings.
Huh?
I told them everything that happened yesterday and...
well both of them felt really
horrible about not being there, too.
They said, "true friends are there for you
during the bad times as well as the good."
"That's what caring about someone means."
So...
They're right.
I thought about how I would
feel if things were reversed...
and, you know...
I think I would have been very sad
if I hadn't been able to help out.
So I feel really bad now for leaving
them out of the loop like I did.
Friendship is a very precious gift, isn't it?
Yes... yes, it is.
Well... I have to go.
Tell Wannai and Awatsuki hi for me, okay?
There you are.
Did you get the information you were after?
Huh...?
Oh... yeah...
All right then...
Are you ready to head back home?
If I'm gonna act on my own...
I'll need to be efficient about it.
First I'll search through all the
databases, keeping an eye out for leads.
They said, "true friends are there for you
during the bad times as well as the good,".
"That's what caring about someone means."
Hey, Sissy. You're going out again?
Oh, um... Yep...
There's something I need to take care of.
Okay, sure.
I'll be back sometime this evening.
Well... come home safely.
You know...
if you need assistance with anything,
no matter how big or small, I'm happy to help in any way.
Just ask me...
Whatever happens, I'm always here for you.
Is there something wrong?
I'm just being stubborn at this point, aren't I?
Sorry... What did you sa...
All right!
Well, here goes nothing.
I need to talk to you.
Huh?
Ah! Yes!
Hey, your towel, your towel!
Huh?!
Easy. Keep it down!
Oh... right, I'm sorry...
but... you're saying...
that Febri was artificially created?
Imagine if your life depended on eating a lollipop.
Whoever it was who made her in the first place...
did they intentionally build that dependence into her?
Probably.
They're beyond Antiskill's control?
Organizations like that really exist?
Well, yes... I think.
Do you have any idea who it could be?
It's possible...
There was this one time...
I got into it with some people who I
think were a part of the underground.
And they were extremely dangerous.
If we're really going to help Febri...
It'll mean taking serious risks
and exploring some shady places.
I want to make sure you understand that.
I hate the idea of putting you in harm's way.
And, honestly...
I don't know how well I can protect you...
With that in mind...
I understand if you don't want to...
First up, we somehow need to track
down the people who created Febri.
Kongo got a look at that guy, so we know
what at least one of them looks like, right?
That's a good point...
Let's fill her in and see if she'll help, too...
And we should check out the place we were
attacked to see if we can get any leads there.
It's entirely possible that the surveillance
cameras weren't working due to the construction.
I'll check to see if there are
any signs of a system break-in.
Also, we can't forget that Febri
needs those lollipops to stay healthy.
I wonder if we'd be able to make them ourselves somehow.
You're right, good thinking...
Do you think you could look into that
Saten, just to see what you can dig up?
And there is also the question of that powered suit.
I'll check with Antiskill to see if
they've been able to discover anything.
Right, that sounds good.
Now, what else...?
Everybody...
Hmm?
Misaka, you've been awfully quiet.
We could really use your help making plans.
It'll be best if we can strike first,
before they have another go at us.
Right.
That sure is pretty. What are you drawing there?
Gekota!
Yeah...? You're doing so well!
When I'm done with this then I'll draw you!
You will, huh...? That would be nice!
We really appreciate this, Konori.
It's great of you to keep an eye on Febri for us.
It's no problem... How's your work coming?
Have you found any promising leads?
From what I can tell so far,
there aren't any signs of intrusion into the system.
I think I'll widen the search parameters a little more.
That's an idea.
Look! All done!
Let me see.
Hi... I'm back.
Oh! How did it go?
You look beat!
Find anything out about the lollipops?
It's about what we were expecting:
"It would be an extremely difficult task
to analyze all the components of the candy,
and even if we succeeded there,
reproducing the exact formula
would be an even more impossible undertaking,"...
So he said.
Oh, that's a shame.
He did say he would get in touch
if he found out anything helpful, though.
Honestly, I'm not sure how
much faith I have in that guy...
A doctor just shouldn't look like Gekota.
Hey, now... be nice, Saten.
The powered suit from the alley?
Yes... There's something we
wanted to check. If we could...
Sorry, too late...
The item in question is no longer here.
Headquarters has taken over investigation of that case...
They left with all of the evidence
pertaining to it this morning...
They took those security robots along with them as well.
You mean the robots from the other day?
The ones that went out of control at the assembly site?
Yeah...
This isn't the first time HQ's
come barging in, guns blazing...
but they were pretty quick about it on this case.
Anyhow, I did get a preliminary look at
what little investigation has been done so far.
But I can't say there's much in the way of results.
The whole suit was a patchwork of unregistered parts...
and there weren't any solid
leads on its footprints, either.
That's disappointing.
I guess there's nothing we can do about it, though.
Well, thank you anyway.
See you.
Hey!
Take this with you.
Why, what is it?
It was lying inside the powered suit...
Who knows? It may be some kind of lead.
Are you sure about this?
If it's gonna be taken out of my hands anyway...
then it makes no difference to me
if it's you guys or HQ who has it.
With that said...
Don't do anything stupid, okay?
Hmm... What could it be?
Some kind of part that got detached, maybe?
It seems like they carted off
every other shred of evidence.
What good is this?
The timing is very strange.
I almost wonder if somebody is
putting pressure on Antiskill.
You mean like that shadowy organization
Misaka was talking about?
Maybe. I wish we knew something more about them, though.
Think hard, Febri... Can you remember anything?
Even the smallest thing could really help us out.
Hmm... Mm-mm.
That's okay.
How did the surveillance cameras pan out?
No luck there.
Right around the time it happened,
the cameras all went dark...
Every last one in the area showed an operational failure.
There's no way! Did you check all of them?
Of course...
The entire area must have
experienced some kind of interference.
That makes sense, if you think about it.
None of our phones were working... remember?
That definitely doesn't seem like a coincidence to me.
Oh!
What's wrong?
I was just thinking...
On that same day, not too far from where we were,
there was some trouble with the traffic signals.
Like the kind Konori asked us to help out with that time?
Oh, yeah! Do you think the two could be connected?
Not necessarily, but it's possible.
This seems like a lot of trouble to go through...
Just to track down a little girl?
Maybe there's more to their agenda than we realize.
We attempted to trace the path of
that creepy man from the other day,
but I'm afraid we have not made any progress.
I see.
Right... It was a long shot. Thank you.
We will continue to expand our search radius.
Be careful, though, okay?
Oh... what about the powered suit?
Have you found anything interesting there?
Well, Antiskill started looking into it...
but they didn't learn anything.
I'll see if I can find out something on my end.
Oh, yeah, didn't you know...?
My father's company has some research divisions
within Academy City that deal in powered suits.
Great... That helps...
Okay, talk to you later.
Was that Kongo on the phone?
Yeah... It sounds like they've
still got some looking to do.
You know, I wonder...
What was this strange man doing
at the Reach Assembly location?
Well, he was looking for Febri, wasn't he?
Hmm...
We cannot allow Mitsuko Kongo to
outdo us in our search for the truth!
We must keep working!
Follow all avenues! Consider every possibility!
We'll keep at it!
I'll look into any blackouts that have occurred
anywhere in the city in the past couple of days.
I've got an idea...!
I'll go back to where we first found Feb...
Mikoto Misaka.
We never did figure out how Febri knew my name...
Somebody must have told her.
Somebody...
Was it her?
But... if it was... Why?
We have taken the necessary measures with Antiskill.
I doubt they'll be able to uncover
anything, the bumbling fools...
still... we can't be too careful.
We don't want them snooping
right before the Reach Assembly.
It's too important to our plans.
We're sure about allowing Febri
to remain out of our control?
We took a vote yesterday.
I thought we had settled the matter.
Just confirming...
We can all agree that we don't want
anything interfering with our big moment.
No need to worry.
Febri will die before the assembly...
She's a back up, after all, and imminently expendable.
The Reach Assembly is almost at hand...
We need to be sure that everything is ready.
So, is it?
Well, people, have we overlooked anything?
Oh, no... Not a chance.
Right, Nunotaba?
All of the pieces are in place.
I will do everything I can.
Looks like Little Miss Condescension got
herself expelled from Nagatenjoki Academy.
I can't find any trail on her since then.
And that means...
I've got just one avenue left.
Hmm...
I've performed an analysis on the
fiber from the capsule you brought me...
And, interestingly enough, it seems to be
made of the exact same components as those
that comprise the girl Febri's body.
To put it more simply... This is a hair.
Hair? One of Febri's, then?
No, it isn't.
This belongs to a different individual.
Somebody else?
Maybe... her sister?
Actually, I'm glad you came by.
There's something I wanted to discuss with you.
I took a closer look at the
candy young Febri's been carrying.
Considering the number of lollipops she has remaining,
I believe her situation is more urgent
than I had originally estimated it to be.
Urgent how?
Roughly seventy-two hours.
That is how long I believe her current store will last.
When they're gone, she'll die.
Oh, no...
Isn't there something you can do?!
It's like I told you before,
if there is anyone who can save the
girl, it's the one who created her.
That's your only real hope, I'm afraid.
Where are you planning to go?
Everywhere!
Anywhere I have to!
One way or another we're going
to find the monsters who did this!
You don't even know where to start.
I... have no choice.
I will ask you once again...
Are you ready to face the darkness
at the heart of Academy City?
It will be dangerous...
You could very easily end up getting hurt, yourself.
If it'll save her...
I'll do whatever it takes.
The quickest way to find out about the underworld
is to ask someone who has connections within it.
If that is what you want...
I will arrange a meeting.
There is something you should be aware of before you go.
The person you are meeting...
is someone with whom you are already well acquainted.
Hmm... Long time no see, huh?
How I've missed you, my little lab rat.
My favorite little lab rat has come back to play.
Hey, aren't you...
Yes...
That one lady...
Yes, that's me.
What's your name?
Therestina!