This time at night?
What's going on?
I'm sorry... There's been a fire in
the first wing of the DNA map analysis lab
that's attached to Shiname Uni...
The cause and the level of damage?
Still under investigation.
Sir! Bad news!
There's a fire at the lab!
At the DNA map analysis lab, yes I already heard about it.
No, another lab!
Huh?
Hm...
The research data at Rangaku Medical Labs is gone?
Bio-labs' system is down!
Can you hear me? Is anyone there?
I can't get through to School
District Three's Thought Labs.
Excuse me, I'm sorry...
There are fires in Shiname's
second, third, and fifth wings, too.
What is this?
An organized terrorist attack.
What method are the terrorists using?
There are no signs of attack from the outside...
And no witness reports of intruders.
It appears... the equipment just exploded.
Hmm.
New information!
The attacks are coming via the communications lines!
We can defend against that.
Block all external communications.
Uh... yes, sir!
They're onto me, huh?
Uiharu would have done a better job at
hacking these guys if she had been here.
But still, that should more or less
take out seventy percent of the operation.
Now I just have to get out there and take
care of the rest of the labs more directly.
Again, Sissy?
I've got to keep going.
At this moment, while I sit here,
they could have another experiment underway.
I can't afford to collapse...
At least, not before the project does.
Oh... Head Resident!
What are you up to Shirai?
You're acting downright suspicious.
Me?
I don't know what you mean. I'm not doing anything...
That's even more suspicious.
Well, see you later!
Huh? Ah!
Sissy!
You're actually home! I can't believe it!
What's wrong?
I'm allowed to be in my own room, aren't I?
Well...
I mean, yes, of course you are...
but it's just that...
you never made it home yesterday.
I had some things to take care of.
Okay...
Well, you're here right in time.
Huh?
Ta-da!
It's Anshindo's special,
limited-time-only sweet-treat summer buns!
Remember, you were talking about
how much you wanted some, so I went...
That's okay, thanks. I'm not hungry right now.
In a little bit, then?
Sorry... I'm heading out again.
You are?
But what happens if the head resident
does another one of her surprise room checks?
Well, if that happens, you can just
trick her again for me, can't you?
Wait, Sissy!
Whatever you're involved in, it's obviously serious...
and something you want to keep hidden...
even from me...
Don't you know I want to be there for you?
Oooh, yummy!
Anshindo's sweet-treat summer buns!
These are super rare, limited-time-only products!
Oh, yeah?
Oh my gosh they look so delicious!
Is one for me?
Well, um... it's just...
Hmm?
You're both welcome to have some.
Really?
But... wait...
You had some of these yesterday, too...
You said you were going to bring them home to Misaka.
Are these the same ones?
Yes, well...
Apparently she wasn't in the mood for sweets yesterday.
But... that aside, she seemed to be doing
fine, so there's nothing to be worried about.
Oh, Wow!
I would recognize those anywhere!
But those are hard to come by! Did
somebody hear me saying how much I wanted one?
That's so considerate!
Why don't you have some with us, Shirai?
No, thank you, I'm okay.
Huh?
Oh, don't be like that!
I'll make some of the special tea I've been saving, too.
Mmm, these are so good!
You can tell they were made by a well-established shop.
Possible arson you said?
Yeah...
There's been a whole series of unexplained fires...
They've occurred in research facilities all over...
We haven't received any requests for assistance
from them, and it doesn't seem to be too serious.
I wonder what's going on.
I would put my money on a bunch of false alarms.
Ah!
I know I had one left!
You ate it, didn't you Saten?
How could I not when you left it wide open like that?
That was a mean thing to do!
I'm heading out...
I think I'll patrol for a bit.
Maybe they haven't asked for our assistance.
But that doesn't change the fact that arson is involved.
I guess if something serious did happen, we'd be too late.
My thoughts exactly.
So I think we should increase patrols from now on.
Nothing out of the ordinary so far in this district...
Huh?
Oh, come on, are you really sure?
I'm really, really sure.
Yeah? That can't be true.
Well, it totally is!
I'm not being vigilant enough.
At this rate I'm not going to
be any help to Sissy whatsoever.
Hey!
This is one, right?
Oh, wow! You really found one, Minori!
Okay, so, what's the number?
Gimme a sec...
You there. Kids.
What are you doing hanging out in a back alley?
Well, ya see...
Looking for lucky cards?
You mean like that Money Card you've got there?
Mm-hmm.
Except it looks like this one's a miss.
A miss?
Look...
It's got a code on the front.
You want one with a code that has a repeating number...
Find one, and it means you're lucky.
One with three sevens in a row is the best you can get...
It will grant whatever wish you make.
They say one person who found one became a billionaire!
So that's it.
An urban legend that grew out of the Money
Card craziness that went on a little while ago.
Huh? But how come?
Why... we aren't hurting anyone.
You might get hurt. This area
can be dangerous. Do you understand?
Get back to your dormitories, all of you.
Aw, no fair!
Also, as a member of Judgment,
it is my responsibility to take
custody of this abandoned Money Card.
Huh?!
Aw, man. Can she really do that?
I'm tired anyway.
Hey! Minori!
Sorry! I'm coming.
What were you doing?
Oh... nothing.
Really?
And this happened earlier today?
Yeah.
Money Cards with lucky numbers on them.
What a funny thing for an urban legend, huh?
Almost childishly adorable.
"Childishly adorable"?
That's rich coming from somebody in that underwear!
It may start out as a cute little urban legend.
But when people get caught up in something
like that, bad things can happen unexpectedly...
Accidents. Fights, maybe.
And let's not forget the suspicious fires, either.
We should all be more watchful.
Fine. It's still a cool rumor, though...
If I got my hands on a lucky card...
what would I do?
There are so many things to wish
for! I can't possibly make up my mind!
And there you go again...
What about you, Shirai? What would you do?
Huh? What're you talking about?
If you found a lucky card that
would grant you any wish at all,
what would you want?
What would I wish for?
Huh. What ridiculous, unscientific nonsense...
This is Academy City we're living in, you know!
Regarding the other facility that was attacked last night,
we investigated.
And we found that somebody physically
broke in and wrecked the place.
There were no human casualties... however...
most of the data and equipment
there were completely destroyed.
At each facility, the locks
were deactivated from the outside.
None of the infrared security sensors were triggered.
And the cameras...
none of them recorded the attackers.
Also, and this is strange...
while the incidents were occurring,
the nearby wind turbines
rotated in the opposite direction.
Hm. Interesting.
This business with the wind turbines...
That could be caused by electromagnetic interference.
Uh-huh...
If she is the culprit, all of our standard
security measures are indeed useless...
What's more, we don't currently have the force
we'd need to stop her once she's gained access.
But sir...
If this keeps up, the experiment...
...will be shut down. Eh?
Sissy! Be still, my beating heart!
You look so sweetly vulnerable like that!
Almost as if you were asking
me to sleep there next to you.
How many days? How long has it been...
Since I've gotten to sit this close
and just look at your lovely face...
Well...
If you found a lucky card that would grant
you any wish at all, what would you want?
There couldn't be an easier question to answer...
I would want...
I would want to be able to help you, Sissy.
Good morning, Sissy. Did you sleep well last night?
I'll just go out there and do my best!
Nothing here...
Aww...
Nothing here, either.
Wha-I thought that...?
But I could've sworn I saw...
Honestly! Weren't you even look...
You're the kid I talked to yesterday...
Are you still chasing that rumor about lucky cards?
No way, it's not like that!
Uh... I mean, I guess it kind of is...
but it isn't.
It's just... well, uh... you know...
I get it now.
You want to find one of these lucky cards
so you can give it to a friend of yours.
It's a generous thought...
But ultimately, it doesn't matter what your motive is...
What you're doing is still reckless.
I know...
But pretty soon I won't get to see her anymore.
She told me that she's moving...
Her parents decided, and there's
nothing she can do about it.
No matter what, I have to give her a
going away present before she leaves.
We've been friends a long time...
She's really nice...
and we hang out together almost every day.
So... I just want to...
Here, use this.
Oh sorry, thank you.
She's a really good friend...
isn't she?
Mm!
Hey, how far are you gonna make us go?
Have some faith in my instincts, will you?
It's nearby...
The lucky card's here somewhere, I can tell.
Let's give up already!
Over there!
Oh, wait... Huh?
Oh, uh, hey, Shirai.
What are you doing there?
That's how you're going to find it? Really?
Just give it a little time, and you'll see...
The nose knows, I'm telling you.
Now... Why don't you come give me a hand?
Okay...
What are they doing? They look ridiculous.
For the record, I was patrolling
like a good Judgment officer...
Despite how it may have appeared.
I am surprised, though.
Huh?
I just wouldn't expect you to help
someone who's hunting for a Money Card.
I wouldn't say I was helping...
I was just looking out for her... making
sure she didn't get into any trouble.
I wasn't doing any more than my Judgment duties require.
Uh-huh...
Wow, Shirai, you might be the worst liar I ever met.
It's obvious that you're doing
this because you want to help her...
So, you were saying?
Oh, nothing at all...
But... what are we going to do?
Do about what?
If we really do come across a lucky
card, it's still classified as a lost item...
so it can't just be given away.
I don't see how we can make it work.
Oh... hey, you guys.
So what in the world are you two doing down there?
Hmm, that is complicated.
Obviously, as members of
Judgment, we can't turn a blind eye.
We have standards to maintain...
But, still...
Hmm. It's true. A lost item is a lost item...
This could be kinda hard to swing.
Impossible, maybe.
Ah! That's it!
I just had a fantastic idea!
Hey, you two... Listen up!
So, um, what exactly is this good idea?
You just leave everything to me.
Uh...
Well, here we are.
When it comes to things like this,
I think the lower tech, the better.
Though... it's a bit cliché.
Ooh! I love clichés!
Konori's gonna save the day!
What do you mean? What's happening?
What's happening? We're searching, that's what.
Huh?
We're looking for something lucky!
A four-leaf clover!
Here we go!
Hey! Wait for me!
Huh? Wait...
Hold on a second, will ya?
You mean we're gonna search this
entire place? We're going to try.
Huh?!
You never know what you can accomplish until you try...
Okay? Give it all you've got and in
the end, you won't have any regrets.
Nothing... nothing...
Nothing here, either.
Yep, it's like they always say...
Happiness isn't an easy thing to find.
Oh, please! Don't say that...
You just have to know where to
look, isn't that right, Shirai?
I'm not so sure about that.
Huh?
Hey you guys, look what I found!
What is it? Did you already find a four leaf clover?
No, not that.
A butterfly!
Oh! There's another one!
How sweet! Those two must be friends!
Sounds nice, doesn't it?
Being able to connect like that...
Being so close to each other
without even needing to speak.
Your efforts don't go unnoticed, Shirai.
They definitely get through to Misaka...
So don't worry.
Uh... What are you talking about?
Why would I be worried?
And it isn't just Misaka, either.
We appreciate it, too.
Yep.
Uh...
You know, you don't have to do everything by yourself.
That's right. We're here for
you whenever you need us, okay?
Uh... what's wrong? Was it something we said?
We're just trying to cheer you up...
I actually found one!
Ah! It's a four-leaf clover!
Amazing! I thought it was gonna be impossible!
I'm surprised I saw it, though.
It's a bit on the small side.
Small or not, it's still fantastic.
Hey... Minori!
Over here...
Found one!
Look! Look! Look!
There are a whole bunch of them growing right here!
Oh, wow, you got one!
Good for you!
Here's another!
That's quite a haul.
Oh, you're getting dressed...
Are you heading out again?
Mm-hmm.
I have some things to do.
Sissy, wait!
Hmm?
Um...
It's just...
Come back safely, okay?
Well, I'm off.
Kuroko...
Thank you.
Sure.
I'll be here.
Waiting for you to come home.
Good luck, Sissy.
Sir, there's been another attack!
That's the third facility tonight!
Hm.
One more down.
So, that means...
There's only...
two to go!
A clover that makes wishes come true?
I only have one wish...
and when you walk back through the door,
that wish will come true... I believe in you, Sissy.