Thank you for waiting.
Hm?
"I hope I have not kept you long.
I am Misaka 10031, your next opponent," Misaka reports.
Huh?
Tch, okay.
You guys get kinda confusing after a while.
Operation confirmed.
Misakas 10031 and 10032 will proceed
with the predetermined course of action.
The time has come.
We will now be commencing trial number 10031.
Tree Diagram has been destroyed.
But how?
Shot down by some hostile force?
An accident with space debris?
Although.
That's not really the point, is it?
The point is, the last chance I had of putting a
stop to the project is now garbage in outer space,
and then there's the fact that the experiments have been
proceeding according to plan, even without Tree Diagram.
Oh, That's right.
One of the facilities on this block was
among the project's transferee offices that
I was looking into yesterday.
Heh.
Thanks for waiting!
Uhh...
Or not.
Oh, hi, On Hold.
You're still here.
So where did she go?
Entry code not recognized.
Entry to outsiders is not permitted.
Please exit the premises.
Hey!
Misaka's sister!
Well.
I don't know why she would be back here, anyway.
Uh... That doesn't look good.
Ahh!
Was that an explosion?
No! Just look! Over there!
Ah!
It's her!
Go! Go!
The Electromaster!
Hey, wait up!
Let's get out of here!
So. You done yet?
Can I go ahead and kill you now? Huh?
That's some pretty heavy firepower
considering we're in the middle of the city.
You should be careful.
Now, what are you running away like that for?
Don't get me wrong, I do appreciate the view.
After all, you've got such a cute little ass.
No.
This isn't close to over yet.
It's too soon to give up.
Yes.
I'll just bring it all down.
Everything they've done.
Everything they will do.
All of it!
There was definitely a loud noise.
But what happened here?
Still no sign of her, though.
It's okay. We'll head back now.
Is that? Her shoe?
I've got a pop quiz for you.
Which technique was it I just used?
Please answer.
Out of the many skills I have to call upon,
which did I just employ to put you on the ground?
Reflection?
Aw, that's too bad.
Yeah. You're close,
but I'm afraid that's not this particular technique.
Would you like to try guessing again,
or should I just go ahead and tell you?
The right answer is...
"Vector transformation".
Kinetic energy.
Body heat.
Or, of course...
Electricity.
Any vector, anything that has direction,
once it touches my skin, I can transform it.
See? Simple.
I'll destroy it.
All of it.
Equipment, research, their greed, their ambition.
I'll tear it all apart.
Until there's no trace left.
It will take time, but someday.
Someday?
Someday it will all be over, huh?
But what good does that do? Before "someday" gets here.
How many more Sisters are going to die?
Shut up!
What else do you want me to do?
End it all? Right now? This minute?
Please, tell me!
How the hell am I supposed to do that?!
Now then, shall we return our
focus to this little match of ours?
Bear with me, 'cause I think I'm
gonna get a little creative, here.
What do you suppose would happen if I
reversed the flow of blood through your veins?
Heh.
No.
Please, no.
What are you doing? Stop!
Tch.
Hey.
So I'm guessing you're the one I'm up against
for this experiment of theirs, that right?
"That's correct. It is a pleasure to meet
you," replies Misaka, offering a kind greeting.
Back at you.
This is my first time going
head-to-head against a Level 5.
I'm looking forward to... Huh?
A gun?
All checks have been completed.
Now...
Shall we get started? Misaka is
excited to begin her first trial.
Incidentally, you've been given
permission to use a firearm, have you not?
You are certain you do not want one?
Hm...
All right, if you're ready,
let's get the first trial under way.
"Yes, please." Misaka is ready.
So," Misaka trails off, commencing her attack.
"Target appears to be deflecting the bullets," observes
Misaka, analyzing the situation with some surprise.
Is the point of this experiment to screw with me?
Hey.
What the hell's going on here? C'mon.
Is that really a clone of a Level 5?
There are some specification
differences from the Original.
However, all of the clones you'll face share
a common memory through their mental network.
Over the course of twenty thousand test runs,
they'll continue to learn and develop.
When you reach the end,
you may find yourself fighting an uphill battle.
That's a long time away, and until then
I'm stuck fighting these losers over and over?
Tch. Man, talk about a buzzkill.
That all for now? I'm getting out of here.
Well.
Actually, the first trial hasn't been completed yet.
And it won't be until you have
dispatched the test subject.
Fulfillment of this experiment requires the
elimination of twenty thousand armed clones.
This subject's actions have not yet been terminated.
Please continue with combat.
"Continue with combat
until the experiment is complete.
Yes," says Misaka, following her orders.
Terminate? Dispatch? Eliminate?
That sounds like...
Huh?
So dark and cold
like sinking slowly down through water.
An ocean.
"So this is what death is like," says Misaka.
That's what you were talking about?
Uh, yeah, that's we were looking for.
Good work today. This concludes the first trial.
It may be dull now, but they'll improve quickly enough.
Just keep hammering away.
There's no need to hold back.
Keep in mind that your opponents
are nothing but wind-up dolls.
Just objects synthesized from chemicals and protein.
Well, then.
Guess I'll go get some dinner.
S... So much... blood!
What's up?
There's been some kind of incident, apparently.
I heard that somebody died!
Seriously? Like a murder?
Hey, how much further is it?
It's right up here.
What's wrong?
Oh, the uh, the body.
It was right there just a few minutes ago.
Huh?
Listen, kid.
You sure about what you saw?
How the...
No way, you're kidding.
Was I just dreaming?
Yes? Is that right? Roger that.
Hey!
Our people have checked all
the security cameras in the area.
They say there isn't a hint of anything suspicious.
Impossible!
I mean, I just!
We're going to write this up as a simple eyewitness
error this time, but kid, you pull this again,
and we're contacting your school.
Man, I'm sick of these brats and their stupid pranks.
What's going on?
What the hell is happening?
Damn it!
M... Misaka?
I am sorry about this.
"It was my intention to meet back
with you after I completed the op, so."
Misaka apologizes with complete sincerity.
Hey, hold on!
Are you... You're Misaka's younger sister, right?
And you're alive.
Heh, heh... I'll be damned.
I must be losing my mind.
Sorry, It's just, until a second
ago, I thought I had found your body.
Heh, ha... I guess I was wrong.
"No, you were correct about Misaka's death."
Misaka confirms your observation.
Huh?
That, that bag.
What are you carrying in there?
"Before saying more.
I must verify your password, please."
Misaka says, as she was instructed.
"ZXC741 ASD852 QWE963, well?" Asks Misaka, testing you.
Uh. Say what?
It does not appear you are able to decode the password.
Given that fact, you have obviously
not been read in to the experiment,
so Misaka cannot say anything more.
That's it!
What the hell are you talking about?
What exactly do you have in that bag?
"It contains Sisters."
Misaka says calmly.
"I apologize for having to leave
the cat behind with you," Says Misaka.
"But I did not feel right bringing him."
"It seems obvious that a violent battle
between humans is no place for an innocent animal."
Misaka says, justifying her actions.
"I appear to have caused undue concern.
That is an unfortunate result of the experiment."
Misaka says, apologizing again.
"But there was no real need to be worried."
"You see, we are many.
All Misakas here are Misaka."
What the hell is this?
Up to now, you have had contact with one Misaka.
Serial number one-zero-zero-three two.
You see, I am that Misaka.
"However, the Misaka who died today
was serial number one-zero-zero-three-one.
She is the same Misaka you ran
into yesterday with Big Sister."
Misaka explains, to differentiate.
"All Misakas have the ability to control electricity."
"And our brainwaves are all linked to each other."
"Therefore, we all share a common memory."
Misaka adds, explaining further.
I don't get it, who are you?
"We are simply cellular clones that have
been mass-produced for military purposes.
The original donor is Mikoto Misaka
one of only seven Level 5 espers in Academy City."
"We are her sisters," says Misaka in conclusion.
Misaka's clones?
Really? But, what is this?
What are you all doing here?
"We are performing an experiment."
Misaka reiterates.
"The details are classified as top-secret."
"So I cannot explain further."
"But it is nothing for you to be concerned about."
Misaka says reassuringly.
"Once again, I hope you will accept my sincere apologies."
"For involving you in this experiment."
Misaka requests, bowing her head.
Now then, if you would look after the cat.
It is just an experiment.
Cellular clones that have been mass-produced for
military purposes from the original donor, Mikoto Misaka.
Experiment? Military?
I wonder.
Misaka, does she know about this?
Project Level 6 Shift.
Test Subject will kill Railgun
one hundred and twenty-eight times.
Thus achieving Level 6.
That's it.
That's what I can do.
The next stop is School District 7,
Tokiwadai Middle School Dorms.
School District 7, Tokiwadai.
So, she's in room 208.
And when you see her, what are you planning to say?
Are you just going to ask her straight out?
"Hey, did you know someone out
there's killing off clones of you?"
It was no use, any of it.
The whole thing is my fault!
I think,
I think there's one last thing I can do to save them.