Let's make a trade, okay?
My name is Ruiko.
Now it's your turn...
Do you think you can tell me your name?
I'm Febri.
Aww...
That's a very pretty name!
Okay, then, Febri...
What else can you tell us...?
Anything goes. You can just pick something.
Mikoto Misaka.
Huh?
What, me?
So, um...
is this little one somebody
you might've actually met before?
No, not that I can remember.
A distant relative or something?
Any half-sisters you've never told us about?
Half-sisters?
Yeah, around ten thousand or so...
Wait...! No, no, no, no, no!
Do not tell me she's your daughter!
No, you would never have done that!
Surely not without telling me fir...
Ow... www...
Hi, I'm Mikoto Misaka...
I'm just wondering how you know my name.
They say children have a sixth
sense about things like this...
Which people are safe and which ones are more dangerous.
Uhh...
Heh. Maybe, but she hasn't seen this yet!
A finger puppet?
A prize that came with a soda...
I don't know how many cans she
drank before she finally got it.
Still into that little guy, huh?
Ahh...
Yo! My name is Gekota!
Your name's Febri, right?
Maybe you can tell me something, Febri.
I would...
Ahh!
You only have a one in twenty-four
chance of getting a pink Gekota!
Ugh...
Are you really going to make a spectacle
of yourself over a lousy finger puppet?
Hey, come on, now, Febri...
You can't just run off with someone else's...
That is so cute.
It's pretty obvious who she trusts the most.
You know... that Gekota isn't yours...
It belongs to Misaka...
Why don't we give it back?
No...! It's my Gekota!
Well, I tried.
Hm. I'm not finding any information on
her under lost children or missing persons.
Nothing at all, huh?
It's too late for me to get in touch
with somebody at Antiskill who could help us.
What are we supposed to do?
Well...
how about I take her for the night?
I mean, just look at her...
I have a little brother, so taking
care of children is nothing new for me.
Well, I hate to impose...
but if you really wouldn't mind...
I don't mind at all!
But, you know...
my place is a bit small...
and it probably wouldn't hurt to have some help...
What do you say Uiharu? Wanna give me a hand?
Yes!
Hmm.
How's it going out there?
Ready?
Yeah!
Lolly...
What's a lolly?
Here... it's all yours!
Should we see if she wants to eat something?
Hey... want some supper?
Boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing!
Boing, boing, boing! Boing, boing, boing.
So, looks like it's time to play house...
Are you up for it?
Totally!
It's time to dig in!
What's the matter? Doesn't it look tasty?
Aaahhh...
Aaaaahhhh...
Good, huh?
Yeah! Heh!
Okay... here we go.
Close your eyes for me!
Whee!
Okay, now it's your turn...
Will you spray some water on me?
Yeah!
Whoa! Easy, now, or you'll fall!
Be careful, Feb...
Ooh... Are you okay, Ruiko?
Ooh! You did that on purpose!
I'm gonna get you!
Hey! Aren't you coming in?
Uiharu!
Hey, Whee-hah!
Yeah! Heh.
I hate to say it, but you seem
to be a finger short of a froggy.
Hey, don't worry. I'm okay...
One lousy finger puppet...
A free prize with a can of soda...
It's... no big deal...
Well, it sure doesn't sound like you're okay.
I just have a lot of things on my mind...
You know, like...
How does a little girl I've never met before know my name?
And, more importantly, why is she so afraid of me?
What?!
Please don't tell me that little
street urchin hurt your feelings, Sissy!
Absolutely unforgivable!
But you need not despair!
I know exactly how to fill the hole
that wayward child has left in your heart!
Huh? Ah!
Hey, Shirai!
What's all the commotion?!
I really wonder...
How in the world does that lost little girl know my name?
So, um...
She's pretty unusual, huh?
Still a cutie, though.
Yeah.
Hmm...
My goodness...! That's an intense flavor.
Yeah! It's crazy, huh?
And she just sucks on them like they're nothing.
Oh, you're terrible, Saten, you know that?
She did the same thing to me last night.
"Hey, this is delicious, you should really try it!"
Oh, let it go. I said I was sorry.
Having fun?
Yeah!
Good to hear.
Yeah, I'm glad you're having fun, Febri!
Heh, heh.
Ugh...
Still no luck.
There's no data on her anywhere.
I put her information into the database that handles
queries from missing persons and lost child cases...
but so far, there's been no response.
We all know what that means, right?
Little Febri here might be a Child Error.
Oh, yeah.
Hi everyone!
Hey, Haru'ue!
We're settled from the move...
So I thought I would stop by
here and say hello to you all.
Well, what d'you know.
So that's where she ran off to.
Ah, excellent.
You managed to find her.
A Child Error. That's what you think she is?
It does seem likely...
I've tried everything, but I haven't
found any other information on her.
Guess we'll have to wait until someone
from an institution can come to get her.
I hope she gets into a good one.
There are good homes and bad homes?
From what I've heard, things can get pretty
horrible, depending on the facility you're in.
Well, maybe... we can choose where she goes...
Hey, Uiharu...
do you know of any sites that rate
and review these types of institutions?
No, they don't really do that.
Hey...! I know!
I've received confirmation.
They're willing to accept her.
Asunaro Park said okay!
It's a facility in District 13.
Don't worry, we've been there before.
We know first-hand that it's a warm, welcoming place.
However, there's one small problem...
They aren't ready to take her in quite yet...
They'll need at least five days.
That shouldn't be a big issue...
I am more than happy to look after her 'til then.
I'll help take care of her, too.
Yeah, so will I.
In that case, I shall assist with childcare, as well.
All right, then...
I'll inform them of our decision.
So... little one...
would you mind sticking with
us for just a little bit longer?
With you, Ruiko?
Yeah...! And everyone else, too!
You mean, with Whee-hah?
Yep.
And Kuroko?
Yes.
And Mii?
Of course. I'll be here, too!
Five days, huh?
That means Febri's going to be with
us until the day of the Reach Assembly.
Oh yeah! Speaking of which...
it's just about time for our on-site security meeting,
isn't it?
I really do hope that you'll come and visit us again.
Of course I will...
Next time I'll bring Banri with me, too...
Bye-bye now, Febri, you be good, okay?
Okay bye, Erii!
Huh?!
Even Haru'ue?!
So help me!
I swear I will get that girl to call me by my name!
Huh. Is this really where
they're holding the Reach Assembly?
'Cause that's kinda surprising...
Yes...
Well, it's one of the sites, anyway.
It's just that this place is sort of...
how do I put it? Sad and uninviting.
The focus of the Reach Assembly is academic rigor,
prioritizing pure research over esper abilities...
The result is an understandable lack of glitz and glamour.
It tends to get pretty nerdy.
That makes sense.
You sound like you're really disappointed about this...
What were you expecting the assembly to be like?
Oh, well, you know... something with
street stalls and lots of events...
Everyone working together to get it all set up...
That sort of thing.
Okay, so that's why you came along.
Yeah, that's pretty much it...
I thought it would keep Febri, you know...
amused... Right?
Right?
Right.
So cute!
My! Look who we ran into!
Isn't that Misaka?
Huh?
Yep, that's her, all right.
What a strange coincidence.
Oh, hey... it's Kongo.
I can see that, thank you...
What is she doing here?
Well hello there... It's nice to meet you...
My name is...
I see.
So Wannai, somebody you know from the
swim club is presenting at the Reach Assembly?
Yes...
We're here to help her set up her presentation.
Awatsuki and I volunteered to lend her
a hand since we're friends with her...
Kongo doesn't know her but selflessly came along, anyway.
It's nothing to fuss about, I assure you...
We'll be set up in a matter of moments...
I'm always happy to help those in need.
So, tell me, Misaka,
is this young lady tagging along
with you somebody's little sister?
Oh, no...
It's kind of a long story.
Come here you two...
You need to meet this darling little
girl... Her name's Febri. Isn't that pretty?
We've only just met... but I can already
tell that we're going to be friends.
In that case, I know that we are going to
be the best of friends, as well, Febri...!
My name is Mitsuko Kongo...
It is such a pleasure to meet you... Truly!
It's really nice to meet you, too, Mitsuko.
Yet another friend...!
My list keeps growing!
Great... Now Kongo, too?
Nice to see everyone!
Have a great day!
Bye-bye!
Okay, you guys... We're headed off to our meeting now.
All right, sounds good.
We'll just have a look around the area.
This should give me the chance I need.
Let's see...
Just give me a minute...
I think it was...
This place is ridiculously spread out, huh?
Hey, before you go... tell me where the bathroom is.
Well, it's...
how about I just take you there?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
Ruiko?
It's all right, sweetie.
I'll be back in a minute. Until then...
Why don't you wait with Big Sister Mikoto?
I'm giving you two a little time...
Have fun, okay?
Wait right there...! I'll be back!
Don't be gone long!
Of all the...
This campus is a big, sprawling mess...
We're gonna need a few more security personnel.
No... I'm totally sure.
This is where it's supposed to be delivered.
On paper, that may be true.
However...
we simply don't have the authority to receive it.
Is there some kind of problem here?
Apparently, this is a delivery for the assembly.
But the student who is supposed
to sign for it hasn't arrived yet.
This school is one of the regular assembly prize winners.
Yes, you're right. It is...
Most of the other regulars
haven't shown up this year, either.
Not here or at the other sites.
It's really kinda' strange.
Hmm...
Hey...
What's the matter now?
It's just...
Maybe I'm wrong, but I thought I saw somebody
from one of the schools we were talking about.
Huh?
I have arrived at the site.
The package appears to have
been safely delivered, as well.
Roger that.
That's all for now.
I'll contact you again once I've located the target.
So, Febri...
you getting hungry at all?
Um-um.
Okay, then. Thirsty, maybe?
Uh-uh.
Hey, look over there, Febri!
Those flowers are beautiful, aren't they?
Why's Ruiko taking so long?
She's one tough customer...
and here I always thought I had a way with kids.
Mm-mm...
I am not going to let this discourage me...
I'm ready to make a sacrifice if necessary...
It's time to call in the super-rare,
one in every sixty cans... rainbow Gekota!
All right, check this out!
Oh, no!
Where is she?!
Ahh!
Aw, man.
Who knew having a job was so freaking exhausting?
Wow!
Well, aren't you just the cutest little thing?
Or not...
Gekota...
I'm sorry!
I just took my eyes off her for a second!
It'll be all right.
She couldn't have gotten very far...
I'll start looking for her, too.
Great, thanks!
Hey, Febriiii!
Is something wrong?
Where are you...? Whee-hah...
Kuroko...
Mii...
Ruiko!
This is it. Target located.
There she is!
Erii...
Mitsuko...
Febri!
Ah!
Ahhhhh... Ah!
That looked like...
Good, you're okay!
Uh?
Ruiko!
Heh.
Oh, well...
I'm just glad she's safe.
No doubt about it...
That's her.
So, it has been quite an eventful day.
I'm so glad that nothing bad happened to her.
It was my fault for not watching her more carefully.
I'm really, really sorry, Saten.
I should apologize, too.
Please forgive me.
Uh... for what?
Come on, now, Febri...
You made Big Sister Mikoto very
worried, running off like that.
You should say sorry, too.
It's okay.
I'm really sorry.
Hmm?
Thank you, Mikoto...!
Bye-bye now!
Ah!
Hey, you...! Get back here!
Ha, ha! No-oo!
I'm gonna get you!
I knew they'd be friends eventually.
They just needed a little while, that's all.
I am glad to see them enjoying themselves.
Seeing them together like that really does
make it worth all the trouble I had to go through.
Honestly, Kongo!
You're going to take all the credit?
That isn't very graceful of you.
Downright petty, in fact.
But I really was helpful this time, I swear!
You just didn't see, that's all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm telling you, it's the complete truth!
Of course it is. I believe you.
Don't say it like that. I'm being serious!
As you know, there are only seven.
Level 5s here in Academy City...
and now, in addition to the fourth-ranked,
we'll be able to experiment
on the third-ranked, as well...
This is truly a stroke of good luck.
Well, in that case, I move we put it to a vote.
Let's see a show of hands...
Those in favor of conducting the experiment on Railgun?
And, of course, I am in favor, as well.
So, next time, Ruiko and Whee-hah
and Kuroko and Mikoto and...
Who thought letting her do the preview was a good idea?
She's still got a lollipop in her mouth!