Come on. They're really late.
I wonder what they're up to.
Well...
Like I said, this group of creeps
is about to start some trouble.
Huh? Hey!
I was just minding my own business!
Hey!
Whatcha keep running away for?
Uh, oh!
Huh?
Hey, now. Wait up!
You're not goin' anywhere.
Look, I need some help. Just hurry, okay?
Okay, okay. Just a little longer!
I've pinpointed the location of Saten's cell!
Good. Nicely done, Uiharu...
Now...
Hold on for just a second.
I have to get my armband!
Huh?
Oh?
Slow down, will ya?
Yeah, just give up already!
Come on!
There, you see?
Start actin' all hasty, and you'll wind up with a boo-boo!
Um... I, uh...
Don't worry, Judgment's on the case now!
You made it! It's about time!
You five are under arrest for attempted assault.
I've never seen anyone teleport before!
If all of us surround her at the
same time, her ability won't matter.
Yeah? Try it. That'll teach you a lesso...
Ah, that's where you are!
I got tired of waiting for you.
What are you guys doing here, anyway?
Who are you?
Uh... wai...
Are you friends with these other little girls?
Since you were the last one to the party,
why don't we get started with you, huh?
Crazy, right? So then she says...
Uh... what was that?
Lightning, I think.
Okay. Can we get going now?
All the stores are gonna be closed.
But, you uh...
Alright, yeah...
Oh, and... Who were those guys, anyway?
Zap people senseless first and ask questions later, huh?
As usual...
Eh?
Home to 2.3 million people...
Eighty percent of whom are dedicated students...
All intently focused on nurturing
and developing their esper abilities.
This is Academy City.
There are seven people who have
achieved the status of Level 5.
Among them, you are ranked third...
The famous "Railgun," Mikoto Misaka.
Sometimes I don't think you really understand who you are!
Huh? What's that mean?
Ughhh! I really have to explain it, don't I?
Sissy, your ability is one people will
both aspire to and be viciously jealous of.
Like yesterday, when your rash attitude
made you those punks' prime target.
People will always fear you to some degree,
and if you're not careful, you'll get hurt.
Hey!
Don't text while I'm talking to you!
It's from Uiharu, she says she just left the dorm...
I guess you should hurry and finish up your
work if you want to hang out with us sometime.
Ah... No fair.
You're always so mean, Sissy.
Man! Whew!
I'm telling you, it was so amazing!
What would you call it, Uiharu?
An instant takedown?
One shot, and she blasted 'em all!
That sounds incredible.
Saten, you're never going to change, are you?
Wandering around those back
alleys always gets you into trouble.
Yeah...
Ah! Well, look at that! We're almost there!
Let's see, where is that invitation?
Yep, changing the subject, right on cue.
So, I'm curious...
Is there any reason we're meeting up at Misaka
and Shirai's school today instead of somewhere else?
Look who it is! Misaka!
Oh, hi Kongo, Wannai, Awatsuki, how's it going!
Hi there, it's so good to see you.
How have you been?
What's that?
Oh, yeah. All of this stuff...
Materials for our summer assignments.
It doesn't really feel like much of a
vacation when they give us this much work to do...
Seriously, couldn't they take it easier?
Tell me about it...
Finding all the material is
almost an assignment in itself.
So, is that why you're here today, too?
Oh uh...
I'm actually just killing time
until I meet up with someone...
I've already finished my work.
Eh?
No surprise there, huh?
Well...
If I had wanted to, I could have finished in a day...
I just prefer to divide the work up a bit.
Oh, whoops.
That is an awful lot of books to carry by yourself.
Oh, dear. How could I be this clumsy?
Don't worry... let me help you with that.
Here, I've got a few.
These, too.
Oh thank you.
Look!
It's Shokuho...
She's always surrounded by her friends like that.
So she's the fifth-ranked Level 5, huh?
How glamorous!
It's no wonder they call her the queen of the school.
I don't know.
I can't say there is a single thing I
have ever found to be likeable about her.
Did I just say that?
I didn't mean to!
I... It just slipped out!
I hope it didn't sound like I was
sniping! I would never want to...
It's okay, we get it.
Well then, I guess we should be on our way.
Yeah, probably.
See you around, Misaka.
Yeah. Bye!
Well, hello, Misaka!
I said "Hello, Misaka"!
Sorry, no talking allowed in the library.
Oh, come on now!
But you were chatting up a storm just a second ago!
You know, I have to wonder...
Is it just that you don't feel like talking to me?
Oh, my! What have we here?
Hey, stop!
You can't just go grabbing someone's stuff without asking!
Oh, no! Now I'm scared!
What's the deal? Oh, I bet I know!
Is it a present for your boyfriend?
What's with you? You tryin' to start a fight?
But why would I want that?
Going one-on-one would be so difficult. After all...
It would hardly be fair.
My tampering powers don't seem to work on you.
I admit, it's a real pain...
that EM barrier of yours.
Listen, you!
Qu... Queen?
Are those two facing off?
That could be interesting!
I wonder what they're talking about.
Like I said, hardly fair, but while going
one-on-one against you would be difficult for me...
Going up against this many of our
finely trained Tokiwadai students...
Well, that would be intense, even for you, wouldn't it?
I'm just kidding.
I'm confused...
Why am I standing around like this?
I don't remember leaving my chair...
Oh, hey! Look everybody! Misaka and Shokuho are talking!
I see nothing's changed.
The way you abuse your ability is still depraved.
And to think that you're the
city's greatest mental ability user?
Misaki Shokuho... Known as "Mental Out."
Honestly, don't be such a bad sport!
This is just a warning...
I thought it only fair to tell you to be
careful about the friends you're making these days.
If you attempt to make any moves into my territory,
let's just say, it's going to cost you. 'Kay?
Shokuho... I've got a question.
Well, go right ahead. I'm listening.
Are you sure that you're really a middle-school student?
That's a good question.
For the time being, at least, that seems to be the case...
But with my tampering abilities, just
about anything could happen, you know?
Hello, Sissy! Uiharu and the others are here!
Come on, come on! Let's go, let's go!
Quit teleporting out of the blue like that!
Hey, you guys!
Thanks for waiting!
Uh... Did something happen to your head, Shirai?
A little over-zealous affection, that's all.
I'm sorry for having to drag
you all the way out here, Haru'ue.
I'm having a great time, really...
And I've got some delicious
looking snacks I brought along, too!
There are a lot of great shops throughout Academy City,
but they're especially famous for them around here.
That's true...
Although I think you enjoyed showing them
off to Haru'ue even more than going to them.
Well, it's nice to share something so fantastic.
I mean, the sheer elegance of the
area is almost palpable, don't you think?
I feel like a princess!
It's like the air itself is scented with roses!
Oh... Is that why?
Huh?
I was just wondering why you went with
that particular design today, that's all.
I don't get it.
What design are you talking about?
B... b... but how did you know?
Oh, it was earlier.
While you were picking out your
cake, I took a quick little peek.
They were so pretty, especially that rose pattern.
You, too, Haru'ue? You are being corrupted!
Just so you know, that kind of
reaction is what makes it so much fun!
How else am I supposed to reac...
Now, now, guys!
Let's not waste our time squabbling with each other.
Well?
Are you coming?
Here to visit someone?
Yes.
All right.
Then please fill out all of
the required areas on this form.
Of course.
Wow, Haru'ue.
It looks like you've got this routine down.
Hey, you guys.
Ah! It's Yomikawa and Tesso!
Hey, what are you guys up to today?
Oh! Visiting?
Yes.
If I may ask, ma'am, why are you here?
Has there been an incident?
Oh, no.
There were some pseudo-radicals we had to take care of...
One of them is being treated here.
He's finally ready to be discharged, so we're
relocating him to an Antiskill-affiliated hospital,
where we can put the squeeze on him good and hard.
C'mon... take it easy, boss.
You were dealing with pseudo-radicals?
Yeah... you know...
All sorts of problems crop up in this town.
You never know what it'll be next.
Yes?
Hey, Banri! You mind if I come in?
No, of course not!
Is there something?
Just thought we would stop by!
You guys!
So delicious!
This is really wonderful, Erii!
Isn't it?
Uiharu took me to the shop where they make them earlier.
You two must have eaten about twenty of them.
Amazing!
It seems like you're doing a lot better, huh?
Mhmm. Slowly but surely...
The rehab can be pretty hard...
But having all you come see me will motivate me even more!
So thank you!
If you can finish your rehabilitation soon enough, then
we can go to school together, starting from second term!
Ahh...
So, uh... Is... anybody else thirsty?
Eh?
Thirsty?
Yes, I could use a drink...
Want to go see if we can find some sodas somewhere?
Great idea!
Well, if you'll excuse us, we'll step out for a bit.
Wait, you mean...
Everybody?
Right... Come along, now.
I still don't understand...
Misaka, what's going o...?
Come on, come on, hurry!
Okay! We'll be back in a jiff...
You guys have fun together!
A soda sure sounds good!
Why it certainly does, Kuroko!
What in the world?
Okay. You want to tell us what's really going on?
Soon enough. Let's get sodas first, though.
So that's it? Their physical therapy?
Poor Edasaki.
She's working really hard, huh?
Sissy... Hello! Sissy?
You zoned out. Is something wrong?
Oh... mm-mm. It's nothing.
You want to plan... a surprise?
Yeah!
I don't feel like simply handing over our gift
will have enough impact, you know what I mean?
It's just...
Well, setting the mood makes a big difference.
What would be great...
Is if we could have it come out of a cake!
Or put it at the bottom of a champagne glass!
But neither of those things would work.
How serious is she about this?
But we could try... Those things!
You mean the...
flowers?
Yes! I call it...
"Operation, Oh, a Bouquet of Flowers?
But Wait, What's This Inside?"
Okay?
Uh... sound good?
Yes, sounds like a great surprise.
Doesn't it? Alright, I'll go buy them!
Do something!
What can I do? You know how Sissy is...
No!
No... Oh, no...
Oh, hey... What is that?
Oh. That's Misaka's bag.
Awww.. How could I be so idiotic?
It'll be okay.
There's nothing we can do about it now.
It won't matter...
It's the thought that counts, after all!
No, we can still do it! Kuroko!
I'll need to use your ability!
You take me with you, and we'll teleport our way in!
You're getting a little over-excited...
Come on!
We gave them plenty of notice!
How much time does it take to
process a simple patient transfer?
It'll be okay.
You know...
Captain...
Wasn't there a guard outside...?
Hey! Stop right there, you three!
What was that?
Come on, move it!
Tesso!
Call below and have them scramble... Hurry!
Uh... Right!
Damn.
Oh... it stopped.
Please note that while the emergency bell has just
rung, we cannot confirm any fires in the building...
Uiharu!
Right!
Huh?
Kuroko?
We're going to look into the situation, just in case.
You and Saten head back to Edasaki's
room without us and wait there.
Oh and one more thing...
No matter what happens, please refrain
from repeating yesterday's little scene, okay?
Uh... Yeah, whatever you say.
This is kind of scary.
I wonder what's going on out there.
I'll take a look and see if I can find out.
Just be careful, okay?
Yeah. Don't worry about me.
Almost!
Hurry up and get it open!
Freeze!
It's no use trying to escape.
There's an all-points bulletin
out on you through all Academy City.
There's nowhere for you to...
Shut up! I mean it! Stop talking!
Captain, their hostage...!
Don't try anything stupid.
If you do, I'm gonna blow her pretty little head off.
The criminal scheduled for transfer has escaped?
Captain Yomikawa is in pursuit...
Reinforcements are on their way.
Where we could really use your
help is preventing any panic.
Honestly!
I can't stand it when Kuroko
treats me like I'm a stubborn child.
She's concerned about you, that's all.
You do tend to be a bit reckless at times, you know.
But, of course, that's what we like about you...
That's right. Maintain your positions.
You heard me. I don't want to provoke them...
They have a hos...
Is something the matter?
What are you doing here?
Why, has something happened...?
It's the pseudo-radicals.
They've blocked our access to the roof.
You should go and find someplace safe.
Edasaki!
Why are you out of bed?
Looking for Erii...
She went to see what was
happening, but she didn't come back.
Huh?
What happened to her?
I'm sorry to have to tell you that...
Your friend's been taken hostage.
Oh, no!
Calm down!
Thanks for helping me...
But they've still got Erii!
What about her?
She'll be okay.
All right...
Where are you going?
Whoa!
What are you...
Come back! Hey, Misaka!
No! Let me go!
Be quiet! And stop squirming...!
C'mon, we're ready to go! Take off!
What?
Misaka!
You've just made a big mistake!
That's my friend you're messing with!
This one has an ability...
All right! Let's give it more power!
I am! My controls aren't working!
She wants her damn friend back, does she?
Well, okay!
Here you go!
I've got to catch her!
Thanks, Saten!
Can't... Hold... on...
Ow ow ow ow ow!
I've... I've got you...
Hang in there!
Oh, honestly!
Huh?
Eh?
I'm okay.
Hey, good timing!
I asked you not to.
But you just had to interfere, didn't you?
Yeah, well...
I couldn't help it, could I? I mean, if I...
No excuses!
Thank goodness! Are you okay?
You didn't get hurt at all, did you?
No... I'm fine, really.
I'm so glad!
It was pretty scary...
Ah!
The bag!
Eh?
Misaka's bag. I had it with me...
Huh?
Kuroko...
I guess we don't have any choice.
Whoa, Sissy! Can we please think this through?
Well, I guess it turned out well enough.
Yeah, you guys saved my skin.
What's that thing?
Oh. I think it belonged to that kid.
That girl with the ability was
seriously impressive though, huh?
So, she must be what people
call an "electromaster," right?
Yeah... And I'm pretty sure that
uniform she had on was from Tokiwadai.
Huh? The super fancy school?
Just a second...
An electromaster from Tokiwadai...
Hey, Kuroko...
Yeah?
Uhhhh...
Thanks for this!
Sissy...
I'll see you a little later, then.
And you're welcome.
I remember!
I've heard about the electromaster from Tokiwadai before!
The best electric shock user in the whole city!
She's the Level 5...
"Railgun"!
Welcome back, pseudo-radicals...
I hope you all had a nice trip.
There you have it...
Looks like she's still the same old Misaka.
Yep, she certainly is.
But you have to admit...
That's what's so great about her!
That felt awesome!
Here! This is for you!
Huh? This? Are you sure?
But that's Misaka's bag.
Never mind! Just open it!
Oh...
Wow, that's a school uniform!
If you keep working as hard as you have
been, I know you'll be wearing it soon!
We went out together yesterday and got it.
Are you surprised?
Mm-hmm!
You guys!
Thank you...
Uh, Misaka?
Sorry, I screwed it all up!
I was working on a better surprise,
but then there was all that commotion, and the
stores closed, so this is what we ended up with, and...
Please, Misaka!
I am really surprised!
And really happy!
Thank you!
Good grief.
There's never is a dull moment. Not in this town.
Misaka is still as amazing as usual, huh?
Yep. All in all, I'd say it was a rosy start...
I wonder what color it will be next time?
Please just leave my skirt alone!