So you're not going to sell out your friends, huh?
No... I would, I just can't talk.
All right... I can't hold that against you.
Moving the Sisters that are being
adjusted would normally come last.
With the abrupt transfer of control
and the watch out for attackers,
they've ignored internal security.
If I'm really going to do this...
it's now or never.
S Processor...
the institute for practical neuroscience?
Yes...
I do apologize for the short notice...
but I wonder if you could come over here right away.
I'll fill you in on the details later.
It's better if we talk in person.
It isn't just one facility...
There are more than twenty.
Are you planning to do this alone?
Yes, I am...
No one else needs to get involved.
I'm the one who made this mess.
I will be the one...
...to clean it up.
She was right about that... huh.
It got quiet in here all of a sudden.
I was sure the Electromaster had finished you off.
It looks like I got here just in time, though...
Hello Frenda.
Muginooooo!
It's so good to see you!
What were you thinking?
My orders were to keep her confined...
You weren't supposed to begin
a real attack 'til we arrived.
Instead, you provoked her and got yourself caught.
What a rookie move...
If you'd listened to me, this wouldn't have happened...
but you were too damn eager.
It's all right. I understand...
You just get like that sometimes.
I know you can't help it.
What do you mean I get like that?
Nice try...
You're the one who's been causing all this trouble, huh?
She blocked it...
No... she blew it apart.
Well, well...
That's a nifty little trick you've got...
running around, sticking to the walls like that.
Almost like you're a spider, huh?
Who is she?
Takitsubo...
You know what to do.
Have you seen her yet?
No, nothing so far...
Where on earth could she have disappeared to?
And why now?
We're way too busy for this.
I guess we should contact those
so-called cleaners, just in case...
I hope this doesn't turn into some kinda' big deal.
Yeah, same here.
Here we are... Time to get started.
She didn't dodge...
No... she's actually turning away my shocks.
Woo... what a show!
That's weird.
I don't know why...
but I get the feeling she's dangerous.
What now? Trying to blind us?
That's not gonna buy you enough time to...
Tch...
She got away... Takitsubo?
Not a problem...
I've memorized the target's AIM diffusion field.
The odds aren't in my favor, going
up against three of them like that.
Shutting this place down comes first.
Oh, crap!
I've overused my ability...
It's failing.
What?
But I'm moving in a completely random pattern...
How could she...
A lucky guess?
No...
not a guess.
She's dodging us.
The target remains whole and active.
Did she jump up onto the ceiling?
That arachnid move of hers is annoying...
Takitsubo...
Mm.
Huh?
Those two are as impressive as ever.
First we have...
Academy City's fourth-ranked Level 5...
"Meltdowner."
And then...
Takitsubo, with the ability to track a target,
even to the other side of the world...
"AIM Stalker."
ITEM's got it made with this
awesome Level 5-Level 4 combo.
Is there anybody who could escape from them?
Aww towd, not vewy wikewy!
Huh?
'ey! I can tawk!
Aaaaahhh...
Aaaah... Aaaah...
I don't know who our mystery saboteur is...
but I do know she won't be at large for much longer.
All we have to do now is box her
in and make certain she can't escape.
She's in the process of raiding that facility...
However, even if she is successful...
it probably won't stall the project.
The people behind it are swimming in deep water...
deep and dark.
This is all the emotional data on the
Sisters that has been gathered up to now...
I'm going to install it directly into their brains.
I doubt they will develop any genuine
feelings from a program this minor.
But it should create a simulated response.
I don't know if this will be enough to
make them suspend the project or not...
However... it should at least show the girls another
path besides the hopeless one they currently walk.
A better path.
Right now the Sisters accept
dying prematurely as inevitable.
Maybe this will inspire some of them to lament their fate.
And when they do...
maybe there will be some researchers who see
them as more than just mindless guinea pigs...
Maybe...
As unlikely as it seems now...
the girls will cry and say they
don't want to fight anymore...
And maybe...
Just maybe, that will touch someone's heart.
It's probably a stupid plan.
More likely than not... attempting this is pointless...
but...
What I felt in that moment up on the roof...
I thought you might actually be an authorized
staff member, so I checked with the people upstairs...
but they said that this place was ultra-off-limits...
at least until the data relocation was complete.
Up to now, they suspected the
attacks were the work of one person...
but it's best not to dismiss the possibility
that the attacks are really a diversion.
Therefore, it is advisable to make sure
all vulnerabilities are accounted for...
Security should be ultra tight and on
alert for both external and internal threats.
So here we are...
and as usual, Mugino's reasoning was right on the money.
There!
Now!
Okay!
Here we go!
Arming the entire facility was a totally brilliant plan!
Sure enough...
no matter where I go, they know my every move.
There's no question...
They've got a psychometrist or a clairvoyant...
One or the other...
Somebody on that team can pinpoint my location.
An esper.
All right!
This sucks!
I'm at a serious disadvantage here...
Although...
Please stop your pointless struggling.
I've got you and now I'll turn you over to my client.
Resistance is ultra futile.
Resistance is futile...
Maybe...
You might be right about that.
This project isn't the only issue.
Even supposing I'm able to put
a halt to the project for good...
How can the cloned Sisters possibly live normal lives?
Their empty, soulless eyes...
Their short lifespans...
Would that not be a crueler fate
than the experiment has in store?
If so, better to leave them be.
And yet...
She's borne the weight of this...
All of it, on her own.
A fool... A noble fool.
Yes.
We are the ones who should bear the burden of this sin.
For good or ill, let them carve out their own destinies.
What the...
Damn it!
It's no use. The installation is complete.
They are all connected by a brainwave
link, referred to as the "Misaka Network."
The emotion program I installed will be shared
by all the Sisters, no matter where they are.
Now... nobody can stop it.
What is that? What's happening?
I'm not entirely sure what's going on.
But if I had to guess, I'd say that
whatever your plan was, it failed.
N-No way!
When did they install that security?
'Kay, so, what do we do with her?
What else? We haul her upstairs.
Roger that.
Come on. Up!
Start walking, you.
Little brat.
Don't move!
If possible, I'd rather not have to fire this.
Now just back up... Nice and slow.
I'm not going to do that.
It's ultra-commendable of you to
shoot something that's not vital...
Especially at this stage of the game.
But unfortunately for you, a simple
pistol can't penetrate my "Offense Armor."
Let's try this again. Please carry her upstairs.
Uh... Right.
Ugh... Damn...
That capsule in there...
It looks like it's got somebody inside.
You should stop looking at things
that aren't related to the job.
You wouldn't want to be deemed a security risk.
Right. Sorry.
Come on, now. Let's make it snappy, okay?
So what do you think. they'll do with her?
Dunno.
And I ultra don't care. We're just doing our jobs here.
If she is of any use, her life
will most likely be spared, at least.
Of course...
I'm guessing that life will be ultra-crappy...
Sad, lonely, pathetic, and stripped
of everything she cares about.
Target changed location.
Twenty meters to the northwest.
Ah! I just can't seem to hit her, huh?
I don't think it's only the way she's moving...
What if she's able to detect
my attacks before they reach her?
The only espers who could do that are...
Are you okay?
Mm-Hmm. Still standing.
Takitsubo's "AIM Stalker" is handy...
but it's a difficult ability to use as
it has to be intentionally overdriven...
It can't be sustained for long.
The target's not covering as
much ground as she was before.
She must be near her breaking point by now.
It's not worth it to use Takitsubo any longer.
If we've pushed her this far, and she still hasn't left...
that more than likely means she has some
compelling reason to make sure this place is destroyed.
If we just wait for her at her destination...
She's sure to show up sooner or later.
She's a wounded beast.
exhausted, but more unpredictable and dangerous than ever.
It's risky, but if I keep my cool dealing with her,
I shouldn't have too much to worry about.
Still...
It's so unlike me to set up an ambush.
I'm rather excited!
Hey, Frenda!
Eh?
Come on, keep moving... Mikoto Misaka...
You don't have time to slack off right now...
Get back on your feet.
Geez, not again!
Fire, fire, fire!
Bye-bye...
Spider girl.
Crap!
I can't dodge!
I knew it...
I suspected as much when I saw her repel one of my shocks.
In the most basic sense...
her ability is actually the same variety as my own.
My Meltdowner should've taken her out.
Is something the matter, Mugino?
So that's it...
I understand now.
Whoa! We've got a woman down!
Are... you... sure... you're... okay,
Ta... kit... su... bo?
Frenda...
take Takitsubo and meet up with Kinuhata.
Huh?
I'll be all right. I can still help.
This isn't just for your sake, though.
Frenda, you took some serious
damage from the spider girl, huh?
You're playing through the pain, but it's bad.
Uh...
And when Takitsubo reaches her limit...
she can't detect enemy attacks anymore...
It's too difficult for me to
protect both of you on my own...
Especially against this girl.
Oh, of course...
I'm sorry we've been holding you back.
It's not like I'm blaming you for it.
In fact, I think you've done quite well...
Thanks to the two of you, our opponent is on the ropes.
Let Kinuhata bring up the rear...
You get some rest.
Mugino...
She was...
...kind of nice to us!
Yes...
I'd hate for anyone to say that I defeated
her because the numbers were in my favor.
Academy City's third-ranked Level 5...
Heh, heh... The Tokiwadai...
...Railgun!
Railgun of Tokiwadai...
why won't you face me head on?
While I'm here doing this, they're out there dying!
Stay the hell out of my way!