I can't believe this...
My path crossing with hers again?!
No, you are all my lab rats, don't you see?
Would you prefer a different analogy...?
Very well, Academy City is my breeding
farm, and all you children are my livestock.
But right now...
This woman could hold the key to saving Febri.
Hmm... Long time no see, huh?
How I've missed you, my little lab rat.
Therestina... Kihara Lifeline.
Ahhh!
Hey, aren't you gonna swim?
Yeah... maybe later.
Jeez. Are you okay?
Hmm?
Ahhhh, this feels fantastic!
Huh?! What are you talking about?!
It's a question of saving face.
Given what happened,
we can't just sit back and do nothing, you know...
If we don't act, and soon, we're ruined.
Getting taken in by...
Don't you wanna swim around?
Floating is fun.
clean up your mess?
Oh, get off your high horse...
I told you you were going to get
paid, so stop your complaining...
Besides, weren't you the one who said
you were pissed about being tricked?
Tch. We can get rowdy if we want?
Go right ahead.
What's the call about?
More work?
Yeah. Can't say I'm excited, though.
Hope you ladies are ready to work up a sweat.
Hmm...
Yeah, what?
Your face is looking more grown-up these days.
You seen your fill of darkness yet?
Has this city made you jaded?
So, how did it happen?
Something hit too close to home...
and you investigated...
You went seeking the source...
and you found darkness.
Then at long last...
you realized that what I said was correct all along.
Academy City is one big test site...
and all the students inside it are lab rats.
Well? What did you want to ask...?
Or did you come here seeking the comfort
of one who knows the truth, as well?
I want to help a friend... to save her.
Huh?
Her name is Febri...
She's a little girl who was artificially created...
If I do nothing...
she is going to die within seventy-two hours.
I'm here for her sake...
I know an underground organization
is responsible for making her.
Given your connections, I thought
you might know something about...
Oh, come on. Don't you learn?
What is it going to take?
You got a whole heap of your own clones killed,
and you still get all mushy
about some girl you barely know?
This kid, whatever her name is,
she's just one more lab rat spawned by this city.
You wanna survive in this town...?
Give in to the darkness and live like livestock...
or become one of the people in charge...
Because those are the only two
options you have in this place.
That isn't true.
I've seen it.
I know the darkness that you're talking about...
At first I felt lost and hopeless...
desperate and destructive.
But you know...
It was the people I met in Academy
City who wound up saving me from myself.
I'm not alone.
I have a group of friends who are dear to me...
and if it weren't for this city...
I never would have met any of them.
There are a lot of things that
disgust me about this place...
but even so...
I can't bring myself to hate it like you do.
Heh.
I've heard enough... You can go now.
No, I can't.
Not until you answer me.
Who was it that created Febri?
How should I know?
What is their objective...
What is this?
You must know! Please tell me!
And what if I lie?
What possible motivation could I
have for answering you honestly?
You and I have a history...
Can you really believe what I say?
Yes.
I'll believe you.
Why is that?
Because right now it's the only choice I have.
Hold out your hand.
Well, aren't you going to eat it?
It's just ordinary chocolate...
Nothing sinister about it.
What's the matter...?
Eat up.
You believe me, right?
I said I'd believe you, didn't I?
Go away.
I'm staying...!
Now tell me about Febri.
You're wasting your time.
I don't have anything to tell you.
I'm not going anywhere until you answer!
No, thanks. I'm done talking.
Tell me about Febri!
What do you have to lose...?
Please, tell me!
Ugh, you are such a pain.
Chemicaloid.
If I'm remembering correctly, that's what they called it.
Called what...?
You mean a chemicaloid is what Febri is?
At the time, of course, it was all just theoretical...
But those boys must have found
some way of making it happen.
These "boys" are the ones who made Febri, then...?
Well, what was their objective?
Hmph. Beats me.
It's probably their elaborate way
of getting their existence noticed.
Getting noticed?
There's some kind of fancy event coming up, isn't there?
An event... Uh...
The Reach Assembly!
They had to artificially create a person in
order to get attention?! That doesn't make any...
Doesn't make any sense?
Oh, yes, that's good. Spoken like a true Level 5.
Huh?
Don't you understand, little girl?
Here in Academy City, you are
one of the privileged elite...
Pin on your Level 5 tag, and
even a pathetic lab rat like you
will have plenty of dear friends
flocking eagerly to your side.
Don't think for a second that you
understand the true darkness of those who lack
even your status in this city...
At the end of the day, you know nothing.
Stupid brat!
What?
You actually met with that witch Therestina?!
Yeah... sorry...
It happened so rapidly
there was no time to tell you guys about it.
So, according to her,
"chemicaloid" is the official term for what Febri is?
And the people who created her are
planning to do something at the Reach Assembly?
She didn't say that exactly. I just put it together...
That strange guy Kongo saw...
the one who was talking on the
phone about "retrieving" Febri...
he was at one of the Reach Assembly campuses, right?
Therestina mentioned an event that's coming up...
I'm guessing that's it.
I'm still confused...
It was the hospital doctor who arranged it?
It was his idea for you to ask Therestina about this?
There's something about that guy's face...
What's his role in all this, anyway?
There is something else he told me
that I think all of you should know.
What's that, Sissy?
He made some calculations based on the
number of lollipops Febri had with her.
Without more, she only has seventy-two hours.
To live...?! Oh, no! That's all...?
Three days isn't very long.
Uiharu?
I'm going to screen everyone
who's involved in the Assembly.
Administrators... participating students...
That's a good idea.
Hey there, sleepy head.
Hello...
Good afternoon!
How is everyone?
We brought something I think
you ladies will be excited about.
Oh, really?!
Were you finally able to get a lead?
Huh? Oh... no... No, we weren't.
We're really sorry.
We searched everywhere for that man. I swear!
All through the city!
But I'm afraid we didn't find anything worth mentioning.
Never fear!
Give us more time, and I know we will find him...!
Anyhow... we're here on other business today.
We came because we have a little present for Febri.
A present for me?
While we were out scouring the
city, we found an adorable outfit.
And we thought...
"Wow, that sure would look cute on Febri!"
Yeah...? Isn't that nice, Febri...?
A new outfit, just for you!
Okay, then... why don't we open it?
Wow!
That's really perfect!
That... that's for me?
Yes.
Mitsuko, Wanna, Atsuki... Thanks so much!
There's no need to thank us...
Anyone else would have done the same.
For Febri!
Yes! Very pretty!
Febri!
Your face is flushed!
Do you feel like you have a fever?
Don't know what a fever's like...
My head just feels all foggy.
Um... A lollipop! Right...!
She's getting worse. We have to hurry.
Hey...
It's him! It's him! It's him!
That's the man we saw...
The one who was talking on his
phone at the Reach Assembly Site.
Take a look, you two. That is him isn't it?
Yes, definitely.
Oh, yeah.
I would recognize him anywhere.
What's that photo from?
The participant list from last year's assembly.
Haruki Aritomi.
Oh! According to this he won the Academic
Reach Assembly's first prize two years ago...
In fact, it seems he's a regular participant and winner.
Wow!
If he consistently wins top prizes at the assembly...
it means that he's one of the most
brilliant people in all Academy City.
This man? Really? That's odd.
I've never even heard of him before.
Of course not...
In a city that's full of high-level espers,
an ordinary genius doesn't really stand out.
Don't think for a second that you understand
the true darkness of those who
lack even your status in this city...
Oh, hey... Something else...
It doesn't look like he's participating this year.
Hey, you know...
that reminds me of something Captain Yomikawa said...
about how a lot of regulars apparently
weren't showing up to the assembly this year.
Let me see...
Yeah... you're right, Konori...
It seems like a bunch of the
usual participants aren't signed up.
Let's take a good look.
Some of these people could be his associates, right?
No relevant data retrieved.
Okay, then... That just leaves Lab One.
Gotcha!
Ahh! Hey! I can't see!
So, little one... Not still feverish?
You really feel all right?
Uh huh!
She had a good appetite, too.
I think we can rest easy for now.
Have you still been searching this whole time?
Well, yeah...
I felt like I needed to do something...
I'm checking out this Aritomi guy...
Apparently he dropped out of
school just a little while ago.
Oh...
that's a shame, huh?
I mean, if he wins those prizes
every year, he must be smart...
wouldn't you agree...?
He could be doing something that's more respectable.
Instead he works for the underground
and tries to abduct a little girl...
I just don't get it.
Yeah... why turn to a life of crime?
Exactly...
I just learned about the Reach Assembly.
But knowing there are non-espers
out there who are successful...
it really gives me hope.
Right, of course.
Yes... If you don't mind, Captain...
That would be great.
Okay.
She says there's not enough evidence
yet to justify taking action...
Oh, well...
That's what we were expecting.
We knew they weren't going to be much help...
not when you consider how much
pressure Antiskill's under right now...
You're pretty quiet...
What's wrong? Is something bothering you?
Yeah...
It was something that she said to me earlier...
Therastina.
A lot of people in Academy City have heard of
the Railgun of Tokiwadai at some point, right?
I've met a bunch of people because of that title...
It opens doors.
So, I was just wondering, if I wasn't a Level 5...
if I wasn't, do you think...
Would it be the same between us...?
I mean, you and all the others...
would we still be good friends like we are now?
Oh, don't be silly.
The reason I'm so attached to you is not because
you're the fabulously talented
Level 5 Railgun of Tokiwadai...
It's because you're the reckless,
stubborn, and a little childish...
but still strong and kind and thoughtful...
Big Sissy Mikoto Misaka.
That's good...
Thanks, Kuroko...
However...
Ahh!
Don't take advantage of the situation...!
And don't call me childish, either!
Th-There's that, too...
I also love how you show no mercy
when you decide that somebody... deserves to be punished.
Heh.
STUDY Corporation?
Yes...
Haruki Aritomi's name came up as
one of the company's lead directors.
Okay, so what kind of company is it?
They seem to do a lot of things...
but mainly it's pharmaceutical
manufacturing and chemical engineering.
So...
do they have any suspicious facilities?
According to what I've found so far,
STUDY Corporation owns a factory in School District 17.
It's an old factory and nothing very special...
but the fact that they paid a
huge amount for it bothers me.
It's not much, but it does seem fishy.
If it's a factory, do you think it could
be the place where they created Febri?
Maybe that's where they made her candy...
If we could at least find out
what its components are, then...
I can think of one way to find out for sure...
Go to the factory and take a look.
We need to move quickly.
The most important thing for us to
focus on now is keeping Febri alive...
which means we either need to get more of
that candy or figure out how to manufacture it.
I have to do this right.
Febri's life depends on my success.
That bridge again...
I know you have your own goals...
Mine is seeing everybody get through this alive...
So... Let's work together...
Maybe we'll both win.
Thinking back on it now...
It's such a naïve, and unrealistic goal to have.
He can dream all he wants...
but is he prepared for the
consequences if we should all lose?
In the end, I guess...
You have to believe in something.
What is it?
There's an intruder in Lab One.
That's unexpected... Who could it be?
I don't know...
The security system just went into Shift A alert.
The security at that laboratory
is intentionally low-priority.
After all, it is a decoy...
It's not surprising that somebody is sniffing around.
It shouldn't interfere with our
plans at this point, should it?
Not if they're just now finding Lab One.
There's nothing there that
can be used to hurt us, correct?
All of Janie's data has been relocated.
The info on the neutralizing
agent is the only thing that's left.
We should make sure...
I'll go have a look around.
You're going to Lab One?
Sounds like an unnecessary risk to me.
I'm not going to do anything heroic...
but we've come too far with this to fail now...
I just want to make sure that everything is still secure.
We don't want any surprises.
Very well. Go.
And once again, there's nobody here.
What the hell?
Just like last time... We were given ultra-bad Intel.
We are still gonna get paid for the job though, aren't we?
What? Those guys?
I didn't expect to see them here!
Did they set up a trap because they knew I was coming?
It doesn't look like that's what they're doing...
Are they working against STUDY Corporation?
Like some kind of underground feud?
Huh?
What's the matter Takitsubo?
Mugino!
Ha! It's no use!
Takitsubo's badass AIM Stalker lets her
track any ability she has sensed before...!
All told...
that makes sneaking up on us impossible!
An ability?
Does that mean that someone is moving those
unmanned powered suits using psychokinesis?
But there's no sign of anybody around here...
Then, how are they doing it...
Maybe... some kind of remote control?
It was lying inside the powered suit...
It seems to be made of the exact same components
as those that comprise the girl Febri's body.
It's theoretically possible that the hair Antiskill found
acted as a sort of receiver for some ability...
If that's the case... and if one person
alone was moving that many powered suits...
They must have Level 5-grade power.
That severely limits who the hair could belong to.
Takitsubo!
Are you okay?
Yeah. I must be tired from swimming.
Sure that's all?
Ugh... I'm sick of this...
Let's just go.
We'll be right behind you.
Come on... We're leaving.
Crap!
What is it...? Is something the matter?
No, nothing... It's okay...
My mind's just playing tricks on me.
Oh? Ahh, I'm all sweaty...!
Let's hurry back to the pool.
That sounds good.
You probably shouldn't swim anymore, though.
Man, look at this place.
They really made a mess of things in here...
I don't know...
I'll be lucky if I can find anything.
Hold on...
Over that way...
An area with functioning electricity.
Stay where you are.
And don't even think about trying anything.
It's you!
What're you... doing here?
I was right, then. You are involved with this.
What is going on...?
Are you in league with these creeps?
That's how Febri knew my name!
You're the one who told it to her, aren't you?
Hello!
Say something, would you?!
Take that with you...
It's the neutralizing agent data.
The what data?
The formula for the candy.
If you act now there should still be enough time.
But why...
why are you giving this to me?
Hmph. Sorry...
I guess you deserve an explanation.
Yes... As you already suspected,
I'm the one who gave Febri your name.
It's all I could think of...
I didn't know who else to turn to.
This wasn't how I originally planned it.
But today...
there was an unexpected disturbance here in the lab...
Fortunately, I was able to get away in time to meet you...
and now you'll be able to keep Febri alive.
You can give her a future.
I'm afraid not.
What you have there is just a dummy formula...
It won't do anything to help with Febri's condition.
I knew it would be a good idea to have some insurance.
So you were the one who orchestrated Febri's escape.
For a traitor, you sure keep interesting company...
Enlisting the help of a celebrity.
Very resourceful... I am quite impressed.
It's nice to finally have the chance
to meet you in person, Railgun...
Put a face to the data I've collected.
And very useful data it has been.
So you're Haruki Aritomi, huh?
Huh? This is surprising.
You seem to have gone to a considerable amount of trouble.
And all just to save Febri's life?
She is a fine product, but even so...
"A fine product"?!
Then it's true. You're the one who created her!
Easy, now...
You shouldn't use electricity.
Unless you want to destroy the real copy of the formula.
Nunotaba...
Inject that into Railgun, here.
It will only incapacitate her...
She won't die.
And what's more...
if you follow my instructions exactly...
I'm willing to hand this over to you...
After all, we have no real use for it at this point.
No, I can't do it.
Inject me.
This is to save Febri's life.
Ha...!
Strong enough to render even a Level 5 powerless.
All right. I did what you asked.
Now give me the data.
Well... about our deal...
It's like I said...
We have no use for Febri...
She is just a spare.
She's a spare?
Yes.
For an invention that's truly revolutionary.
We call it Janie.
I knew you were involved in this!
Care to explain yourself?
To tell the truth...
It's a long, complicated story...
See, once upon a time...
Come on! This is no fairy tale!