Excellent.
It looks adorable on you.
Very soon, you'll be going outside on your own.
Shinobu?
Remember...
every once in awhile, suck on one of these.
And now there's... one last thing.
Mikoto Misaka.
Don't forget that name, all right?
Mikoto Mi...
That decision was it...
The beginning of everything.
What happens now?
Have I finally done something to help...
instead of causing more harm?
Honestly.
She is nothing but trouble.
Hmph.
We have some uninvited party guests, do we?
Poor things...
facing down twenty thousand powered suits...
I think we can handle one or two gawky teenagers.
Sorry to keep you waiting... Hi.
Heh. You know, you're late.
Hey, guys!
Wha... Who are these people?!
You've disrupted the peace of Academy City.
You've hurt our friend. An innocent little girl!
This shield is a symbol of duty.
And that duty... is to stop you!
You may have Antiskill under your control...
But they're not the only law in this town.
I think today we'll do this Shirai style.
Huh?
Judgment is on the scene!
That's right!
Mikoto?
Oh, uh... it's nothing.
Okay, guys... I'm counting on you.
By all means, come and get it...
I am Kuroko Shirai, Sissy's right-hand gal...
And by my pledge...
None of you shall set foot past me!
You're up!
Tank squads E and F, come to the left flank!
Squads J through M, switch off! Let's go!
Careful now!
Don't forget our main objective!
To prevent these things from leaving the premises!
We're buying time!
Misaka is sure to come up with something!
I, for one, am glad... that
these machines are running with
simple, easily-controlled programming.
First, you have to select a target.
Then it's all just a matter of maintaining aggro!
Whoa!
Awesome!
A water current and buoyancy control combo!
Hi, Kongo!
Those are my friends.
Don't you even think about harming them.
I simply won't allow it!
You're not gonna get by me!
Me, either! We're doing this for Febri...
and also... Because a good friend asked us to!
This is for Misaka!
Take that, robot!
I'm kicking it up a notch today!
Shirai!
Because today...
I don't just fight for Judgment.
I fight for Sissy!
They're better than I had expected.
Yeah, well... Our attrition rate is
still running at less than two percent.
I want to know where Railgun is.
Once you do find her... let Kosako and Madarame loose.
Nunotaba!
I'm increasing Janie's operating ratio.
Keep everything regulated!
Why did I do that?
Of all names, why did I give Febri that particular one?
Is it because I believed in her?
Yes...
Maybe that's it... I just hope... I'm right.
What's that?!
We have an intruder!
Is that...
Railgun?!
But... how did she find this place?
Damn that girl.
Hello, Railgun.
Excuse the mess.
I didn't expect company,
but I guess you negotiated your own invitation.
Shinobu? Shinobu!
And now that you're here, I'm afraid you leave us
little choice. Please enjoy our hospitality.
Just hold on a little longer...
We'll see her soon enough.
All you espers have one common weakness...
You're only human, which means you will eventually tire.
And you are no exception to this rule.
I don't care what level esper you are...
When you're this outnumbered...
you don't stand a chance.
Yeah, you're right.
If I was all on my own, this would be difficult.
However...
Things are different this time.
All of us...
are fighting against you together!
Incredible...
We have planned for this situation...
Activate scenario B-7...
Send Kosako and Madrame, now!
Squads A and B, hang in a little longer...
Espers, attack!
Go once again from the left flank...
Hah!
Okay. Who's next?
What do we do, you guys?
We can't get through to the others!
There's no signal!
I expected this.
I don't know what to do!
The commands to my security robots aren't...
Yeah, seriously...
What now?
It's time you learned a lesson.
Intellectual prowess cannot be neglected...
or we will all become helpless
sheep in thrall to the espers.
It would have been a lot more satisfying
to have gone up against Railgun...
Well...
what are you gonna do?!
You seem to be getting worn out, Railgun.
Unfortunately for you, this party is just getting started.
These models are equipped with weapons made
after analyzing the city's fourth-ranked esper.
I guess you could call it our version of Meltdowner.
Enjoy your first-hand look.
Uiharu?!
No, I'll be all right...
Please, don't worry a...
Behind you!
Sorry we're late.
Your friend suggested that I bring this along.
What is it?
Let us take care of contacting
the other sites, okay?
It's Haru'ue!
That's right... and Banri is helping out, too...
We're making a network of telepaths.
I thought something like this might happen...
Thank you for this.
Please, it's no problem!
Being able to help Judgment out
is like a dream come true for me!
"Always be prepared and you will never be surprised."
Philosophy in action.
Isn't there a manual for this?
Yeah, don't worry. It's in my head.
Well, mostly.
Okay then, here goes.
Allow me to introduce the variable-form, large-scale,
all-purpose machine built with the latest technology
from Kongo Airlines' Metalworks Plant Number 2.
What is that thing?!
What do you think of her?
Ecaterina the Second! New and improved!
That's what she calls it!
Whoa! Nice choice, Uiharu.
You're fired up today, huh?
Okay! Let's see if we can do them justice!
It's so fast!
Ready, and... Knockout punch!!
Saten, be carefuulll!
Fire!
Oh, please!
That's nothing like the real Meltdowner.
Damn! Damn every last esper!
This is a day of revolution!
I'm taking over control now, Saten.
Okay!
You hate espers? Well, I'm actually a Level Zeeerooo!
Are you serious?
That was a poor, pathetic imitation.
Oh, quit it.
I'm damn sick of these pieces of junk.
Whoa! Just like our Intel said!
It really is copying Mugino...
That's just plain asking for it.
This is an ultra huge number of powered suits...
What do you think is going on?
Who knows?
So this is what's behind all those
fool's errands we've been sent on lately.
Damn it...
You bastards were using us
this whole time to collect data?!
Screw you!
Whoo-hoo!
Ultra-pretty fire.
Hey, Mugino... Over there I sensed...
Hmph!
We don't have time to waste on a spoiled
little brat who doesn't want to learn her lesson.
Hey... Those people earlier...
Oh, those guys...
It's best to forget about them... okay?
We need to hurry!
Madarame! Kosako! Do you copy?
Not getting anything from above, either.
It's not over!
It isn't over!
We have not been defeated!
See, that's where you're wrong.
You!
I suggest you put an end to this...
and let Janie go this instant.
Shinobu!
Hi, Febri...
Well, I came. Like I promised.
This disgusts me...
Espers reveling in their triumph!
Aritomi! What are you?
Code input confirmed.
Initiating final phase.
Janie!
Huh?
They stopped the attack?
Sissy...
N-N-N-N-N-No! Don't, Aritomi!
You can't be serious about this!
You're setting the system to a runaway state?
If I force the connection to break,
she will die.
This is the final phase...
also known as the last possible resort.
I'm going to turn Academy City into ashes.
Oh, yeah? And what exactly are your plans?
Seriously now...
you really think I would tell you?
What are you doing?
There's not much time left... I hope you're ready.
It-... it's time to die...
Oh, no!
I can't... It's no use...
What am I going to do? It's over!
You want to take the easy way out?
I'm not gonna let that happen.
You know, there was somebody I met once...
He had all the power he could ever
need, but still he reached out for more.
I also know someone who was a lot like you...
ashamed of her lack of ability.
She was willing to do cruel things...
to make up for her perceived inadequacies.
And then there's this group of girls I know...
They thought of themselves as tools.
And quietly accepted an inhumane fate.
And let's not forget the biggest fool...
The reckless, stubborn girl...
who thought she could make everything
better by throwing her life away.
Now here I am... I finally figured it out...
Life isn't about being strong on your own all the time...
See, I made a promise to my friends...
That no matter what, I'd help Febri.
And protect the city.
I'll keep that promise. Even if it means saving you.
So that's it.
Now... what do we do to abort...
This is why...
Answer me! I knew I could... believe in you.
I... I don't think...
It's too late now...!
The final phase can't be stopped!
The plan involves scattering
five thousand filaments in the skies over Academy City
and then running the Diffusion
Ghost ability out of control,
triggering a decay chain in the AIM diffusion fields
that fill the area!
The launch mechanism is in some
construction equipment in stationary orbit
thirty-five thousand kilometers up.
The missile has already been launched.
Every second, it travels seven kilometers closer to us...
So... It cannot be stopped... Not by anyone...
Certainly not by you!
You're right... I doubt I can stop it.
Not all by myself.
A missile?!
How can we help?
Give me its specifications...
It's Ruiko!
Shinobu, this is Ruiko...
Just a sec, okay?
Judgment has its share of science students.
I'll ask around.
Yeah, do that!
I will help out, as well.
Hey... Febri is looking flushed.
Huh? Show me your lollipop!
I guess it's all gone.
Tell me she has some left!
That was the last one!
Oh, no!
Let me handle this.
It isn't a matter of "can" or "can't."
I will find a way.
I'll do this somehow.
Anything is possible.
Because I know I'm not in this alone.
Aghhhh! Man!
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
Using Judgment's system,
not only is there no way to intercept it,
I can't even compute its orbit!
Given the machine's specs...
I would've thought that will be a simple process.
"I have heard about what's happening...
It looks like it's finally my turn,"
says Misaka, announcing her intentions with superb timing.
It's an ingenious design...
When the missile's warhead reaches thirty thousand meters,
it's set up to then subdivide into five thousand
micro-warheads.
Once that happens, it'll be too late.
So it's imperative that the missile be shot down
before the split occurs.
And the only way that can possibly be done...
I made it! I'm here!
Lollipop?
Thank goodness. This'll buy us a little time.
They were exactly where that Aritomi man
said they would be. What now?
First, we need to free Janie from
the runaway system, and to do that...
We're going to need Febri's help.
Right now, she's in a state where she will accept
no outside input...
but if we can get a strong emotional response
from Febri, who is basically identical to her...
That makes sense... Because when all else
fails, love can still get through, right?
Huh? Uh... okay... Yeah.
It took some doing, but I had Kongo rig the airframe
so that all eight thousand and ninety-two jet points
will activate to a precision of
one one-thousandth of a second.
Theoretically, This should work out... but...
How did you get such a complex
calculation done in so short a time?
Oh, well... you know...
Sorry, Kuroko.
I never had any intention of dragging you into this.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I'm really glad... There's nothing that could make me
prouder than having you rely on me to assist you.
Your confidence means the world to me.
Thank you.
They're in synch. Okay, Febri's up.
Got it...
Big Sister, it's Febri! And this guy here is Gekota...
He's a really good friend of mine.
You know what? I've been outside...
Please work...
I know I'm asking for more than I deserve at this point.
If not for me... for them...
Let Febri's emotions get through to her sister!
This processing speed can't keep up!
What's that? Access from outside?!
"I will give you a hand, okay?"
Asks Misaka, retroactively seeking approval after
having already acted.
Why would you do this?
To say thanks for the fragments
of our mind we received from you.
Your mind? I...
By the way...
This Misaka's serial number is 19090.
Wait, do you mean... What I did before...
it reached you?
That's right... and, moreover...
those two young girls have a thought base
program that is identical to the Misakas'.
Which means they are basically
like family to the Misaka sisters...
"Does an older sister really need a
reason to help out her younger sister?"
Asks Misaka, adopting a tone
of wisdom and sisterly affection.
Like those girls, we, too, want to know...
how bright and beautiful the world can be...
when you are not alone.
Good morning, Big Sister!
Shinobu! Big Sister finally woke up!
She did...
Good morning... Janie.
Go on now, Febri...
You have something to give her, don't you?
Oh! Here!
Take it! It's for Big Sister and for you, Shinobu!
Do you like it? I made it myself!
You made something... for me?
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing... There's just so much to do...
So many beautiful things I want to show you.
I can't take it!
It's just, she's growing up so quickly!
Come on, Saten, stop!
You promised that you wouldn't
cry, and now you're gonna make me...
Ruiko, Whee-ha, don't cry. It'll be okay.
Here, Janie. I brought this for you...
It's a good luck charm... Keep it with you.
I promise, it's quite effective.
Guess that's it, then... So they'll be going to a
facility overseas to be examined and reconditioned?
That's too bad...
now that we've all become such good friends.
It's difficult to believe how well everything turned out.
Almost like the bad parts never happened at all...
as if the record of events had been completely rewritten.
Oh... Really?
Electronic records can be so...
Well... unreliable, would you say? Anyhow...
I get the feeling that some of the
human memories have been doctored, as well.
Oh, um, yeah...
Well... if you're willing to put differences behind you,
swallow your pride, and reach out... the results can be...
Impressive...
I guess it's my turn now, huh?
It'll be okay... I know I can do this.
After all... I'm not alone anymore.
You're ready?
Yes.
Okay... should we get going?
If we leave now we'll be in
time for the afternoon lectures.
Yeah, you're right.
I think I'll stop for lunch somewhere.
Man, this city...
There's never a dull moment, huh?
Not when you're around, Misaka!
Hey, hold on...! What's that supposed to mean?!
So... is everybody ready for the regional field trip?
Is it that time already?
Liberal Arts City, huh? I can't wait!
Wait, come on!
Seriously, guys! What did you mean by that?