An after-hours pass request? Really?
Um. Yes!
After making such a pathetic excuse for
being out all those nights without permission,
you ask for this?
You've got some nerve, don't you?
All of the necessary paperwork
does seem to be accounted for.
As it happens,
I received a virtually identical request from Shirai.
It was dated tomorrow, and had the same
reason for absence "a study group with friends."
Oh, yes. Kuroko and I are both...
What are you two scheming?
Nothing, I swear!
We're just studying with some friends.
Hm. Can't you study in the dorm?
Why do you need to leave the premises?
I guess you could say, for a change of pace?
These friends are from another school,
and we're all really loaded up
with summer vacation homework.
You know?
Very well. You may go.
Huh?
I hope your study group is productive.
However, if you are even one minute past your return time,
you know what is going to happen.
Don't you?
Uh... yeah!
A good day to you Uiharu!
What's happening?
I've got good news!
Misaka and Shirai both got their after-hours passes!
Oh, really?
That's fantastic!
They said getting approved might be kind of tricky.
But, I'm glad it worked out.
So that means we can proceed with
today's study group as scheduled!
It's been so long since we've all been together!
Mm-Hm. Heh!
And Misaka will be there, so it's the perfect
opportunity to find out who she made those cookies for!
Behave yourself, Saten.
We aren't entirely sure she gave them to a boy.
Oh, I'm completely sure!
There was a look on Miska's
face that I've never seen before.
There we have it. All ready!
And now we put them in the oven.
And then we just have to wait
a little while for them to bake.
I hope I'm not putting you out.
It's really great of you to let me use your kitchen today.
No, it's not a problem at all!
Though for something like baking cookies.
I would think your dorm would be
better equipped than my lame kitchen.
Oh, um, not really.
When it comes to prying eyes,
my dorm has more than its share.
You know?
Mainly Kuroko, Kuroko, and Kuroko.
Ho-ho.
So this present you're preparing is for someone
you don't want other people asking you about, huh?
No, that's not it!
I'm in this person's debt, and I
don't like being indebted to anybody.
I would have thought store-bought would be
good enough, personally, but the idiot said
something about how cookies are best if homemade.
I'm not doing this 'cause I feel obligated.
I'm just tired of listening to all the
whining, and I thought this way it would stop.
Well, then. Good for you.
Uiharu and I have been concerned
about you for a while, Misaka.
And you know poor Shirai's been distraught.
Ehh...
I understand if I'm not the person you want to confide in,
but I hope you know I'm always here if you need me.
I'm sorry. It's just...
I'm the one who caused the problem in the first place.
I didn't want to drag anybody else into it.
Looking back on it now.
It was almost more than I could handle.
I'll try to be more careful.
I'm really sorry.
Great.
Anyway, you seem to be feeling a lot better now.
Having a new boyfriend can do that, huh?
Boy? Uh n... no. I don't have a boyf...
Ah! Oh, no, the flour! Whoa, and the eggs, too!
How adorable.
She sure made a mess, though. Heh, heh.
It wouldn't be very nice to try to force
the information out of her, Saten.
Yeah, yeah. I know that.
Once we're finished up with our Judgment work,
Shirai and I will do our shopping and head over.
As for Haru'ue, she says she has something to do,
so she'll be a little late.
All right. I'll get things ready here.
That sounds good. I'll see you later.
Hey Shirai!
How has your morning been?
Good so far.
Lots of free time on your hands again, huh, Misaka?
Just a minute, when you say it like that,
you make it sound like I'm a loser.
I'm just taking it easy now
because I have plans later in the day.
You've been skipping meals in the dorm a lot lately.
What have you been up to?
You know, a little of this, a little of that.
A lot of the time,
Shirai came here and just ate by herself.
I know.
Hm.
It sure is peaceful now.
That whole Money Card situation seems to have settled down
and the back streets and alleys of Academy City
have finally returned to their usual calm.
Cute! Where did you buy that?
I can show you the store now.
Really? That would be great!
I found one!
Whoa! Another?
See? Isn't this place amazing?
Not for me.
I've only found three-leaf ones.
Judgment lady!
How are you doing?
Long time no see.
Here, take a look!
When I told my friends about the clovers,
they all wanted one, so I brought them here.
That was nice of you.
I don't want you guys staying out here too late, though.
Mm.
Found another one!
I finally found one! It's got five leaves!
Let me see! Let me see!
Look!
Oh!
Yep. Things are nice and peaceful.
Tough homework?
Yeah.
There was this book report I was assigned,
but I'm not sure what I want to write it on.
There's not much time until the vacation's over.
I know, don't remind me.
There are still so many loose ends to wrap up, too.
Ah, not again.
What's up?
Someone is trying to crack into the newspaper
club's server at Sakugawa Middle School.
I was asked to look out for it.
We have a hacker.
This seems to be happening a lot lately.
Why would they even want to go after
a middle school newspaper, anyway?
You know how hackers are.
They're always after a challenge,
and you are one of the best goalies in the whole city.
Huh? Did you say something?
Ah, they broke through the firewall again.
That's pretty impressive.
You're almost in now. Keep trying!
Uh, "keep trying"? You're rooting for them?
No, it's okay.
The server itself is actually a trap.
I just have to log the hacker's IP
address and send it on to Antiskill.
Ugh.
Maybe I should try to find a different book to read.
But I'll probably just have a
hard time with that one, too.
The legendary digital goalie of Academy City.
Brought low by a book report.
What was that?
You say something about a goalie?
Never mind. There anything I can do to help?
It's so sweet of you to ask!
Oh, well, this isn't about the book report.
But maybe you could help me out.
Do you happen to know of a supermarket
around here with a good selection?
Supermarket? What for?
I'm going to a study group after this.
We're each supposed to pick up an ingredient at the store,
then we're meeting at Saten's place.
There we go.
Hm...
Oh, would you look at that!
Uhh...
Hello, Shirai.
Such a small world, isn't it?
Lovely. It's Kongo.
Doing some shopping?
Yes, I am.
So, what are you in the market for?
Just getting some food, that's all.
What a coincidence!
That's what I'm doing, too.
I could accompany you.
I don't mind. It isn't too much out of my way.
Oh, but I would hate to
inconvenience you in the slightest.
I'm sure you have a very busy day
of snobbery and condescension planned.
I felt it was my civic duty to approach you.
You just looked so lonely out here,
shopping without a single friend by your side.
Interesting you should say that, considering that
you appear to be shopping all by yourself, as well.
I am doing no such thing, thank you.
In fact, I'm going to meet up with
Wannai and Awatsuki in a little while.
I mean, we don't have plans, exactly.
But they'll be done with swim practice shortly.
Until then, I'm just passing the
time with some personal shopping.
Would it help if I clarified
the definition of "alone" for you?
Now, just come with me.
There is a fantastic shop over
here that is one of my favorites.
Huh? Hey!
Why are we in a pet store?
Yes!
The selection here is every bit
as good as I've come to expect!
Hey, um, Kongo.
Oh these are nice and plump.
They should be the perfect size.
I'm confused, here.
Would you mind holding these for a sec?
Uh... Ahhh!
I thought you said you were out shopping for food today!
Ecaterina will be happy.
She has a very sophisticated palate, you know.
And this "Ecaterina," would be...
that giant python?
Turtle?
Heh.
Ah.
I'm guessing you're here about the girls?
Yes.
I'm sure you'll be happy to hear
that they're all doing very well.
That also includes the one who was injured.
She seems to be making good progress.
On the surface, anyhow.
What does that mean?
Following my initial examination,
I have learned a few things.
As we suspected, they are clones,
created from the somatic cells of the Original.
Which is you, of course.
During the creation process, various
drugs were administered to the culture fluid.
These drugs promoted the rapid growth of their bodies.
They developed incredibly quickly from fertilized
eggs to their current form in a mere fourteen days.
The girls already have shorter
lifespans than ordinary people,
but the accelerated growth process
has shortened them even further.
Ah! Shortened? How much?
Hm. I can't really give you an exact timeline,
but I would guess that, at most,
they have another year or two.
Oh, no.
Which is why they need to be adjusted.
Adjusted?
Here, take a look at this.
What we'll do is balance the hormones that promote rapid
growth and regulate the rate
of division of the cell nuclei.
By doing so, we should be able to
recover a certain degree of their lifespans.
We can't cut so many young lives short, can we?
We're currently in the process of dividing this
research among organizations outside of the city.
There will be constant
communication between these facilities,
ensuring that everything that can be done for them is.
Outside facilities? That sounds perfect.
The fight for those girls will continue.
And it may be a long road yet.
Although, at least this time it won't be a fight to die,
but rather a fight to live.
Hmm. I just don't know.
I wonder what everybody else is going to bring.
I'm so excited!
I've found the ultimate ingredient for tonight.
Sparkling clean.
Oh, man. I'm running late!
Kuroko's probably there by now.
Table for one?
No. I'm meeting someone.
Huh?
Uhh...
I'll be right back with some water and a menu.
Oh, no! Please don't!
I'm not with them.
I knew there was something I didn't like about this place.
Apparently they cater to spoiled,
sheltered little princesses.
You know, that fight was far from a clear victory for you.
Huh?
To be fair, it's an issue of prior information.
If I had known you were the Railgun,
I would have taken more care setting up my stuffed doll-
Frenda!
Huh?
You haven't forgotten that it was because you neglected
to clean up those very same dolls
that she was able to get away, have you?
Ah! Oh yeah, I guess that's right, huh?
Owwww!
Clean up your messes, bimbo!
What's going on here?
If you are going to fight, take it outside the restaurant.
As a Judgment officer,
I cannot allow you to disturb the other cus...
Sissy! I'm disappointed in you!
You know better than to start a
dispute in a public place like this!
Hey, hold on! I didn't start this.
I was just waiting for...
We've discussed this sort of thing so many times before!
You can't get into fights with
members of the weaker general population.
Excuse me, who are you calling weak?!
What are you, a fourth-grader?
Heh.
I'm certain you aren't talking to me, as I
am quite clearly a full-fledged middle schooler
who was only speaking out of a
serious concern for your welfare.
Angering Sissy here is very dangerous.
It could cost you your life, in fact.
Like I said.
You should really keep your nose out of this, little girl.
Your friend would be the one
shredded to bits if we got into it.
Just like I thought. You don't know anything.
I'm sure you'll revise your opinion
knowing she's the Railgun of Tokiwadai.
Well, Mugino has more combat experience than her.
She would blow your friend to pieces.
Sissy will rip her apart.
Mugino will win!
The victory will go to Sissy!
Mugino!
Sissy!
Hold on, Kuroko.
Take is easy, Frenda.
Okay, fine.
Sissy may have cartoon characters on her underwear,
and her taste in general does tend to be more childish
than one might want.
However, as Tokiwadai's Ace,
she is still quite a formidable opponent!
Yeah, well, Mugino may have her flaws, like a shrewish
temper and a tendency to flaunt
her underwear to passersby,
but in a fight she's completely unstoppable!
Honestly!
You think your flat-chested friend
can win against this kind of power?
How ignorant to think that size matters!
When it comes to future potential,
Sissy is the clear winner here!
Get your hands off of me!
Man. I'll never be able to go to that restaurant again!
Wait for me, Mugino!
Hey, we're here!
Ah. Come in!
Shirai, you look a little disheveled.
Heh. Oh, it's nothing, really.
Ta-da!
Ooh. Nice stewpot!
Yep, I borrowed it from a friend of mine.
And I've got the stock all ready to go.
Wow, that's exciting.
I bet we're the only ones in town having
a stew party in the middle of summer.
Now let's be clear. This isn't a party.
It's a study group, as is written on our permission slips.
Oh yeah, right.
Well, whether it's an official party or not,
eating hot food when it's hot
outside is good for the body.
Okay, so what ingredients did everybody else bring?
Well, actually I had a hard time deciding what to get.
But the man at the meat counter suggested these.
So I went ahead and got them.
Boxes?
Hmm...
Wow!
They're full of great-looking beef!
The marbling is incredible!
Um, is that good?
Not good, Misaka. Wonderful!
What about you?
Oh! Here, take a look.
I decided to go with vegetables.
I focused on summer veggies.
Stuff that's in season, like okra and corn.
And also some mushrooms and tofu.
Great idea!
Sounds delicious and full of vitamins!
I'm up next.
I've brought something that can enhance
a young lady's natural beauty!
You should prepare yourselves,
because I think you're going
to be very impressed with my contribution to the pot.
Sounds interesting, Shirai.
What did you bring?
I admit I was unsure at first.
There I was, standing in the pet
shop with plump mice in my hand,
not certain what to do.
Plump mice?
You went shopping at a pet store?
However!
It wasn't long before I had an epiphany!
And I knew I'd found an ingredient fit for Sissy.
Are you going to tell us what you got?
Yeah, Shirai we're on the edge of our seats, here.
The ingredient that I chose is turtle!
Turtle?
The soft collagen will enhance Sissy's fresh,
youthful skin, making it even more beautiful than before!
And that's not all!
That looks like...
Fresh soft-shell turtle blood!
Mixed with apple juice, to make it easier to drink.
Go ahead, gulp it right down!
One glass and you'll be full of energy.
No, you'll be positively bursting with vitality!
It's possible you'll be so fired up that
you won't be able to get to sleep tonight.
When that happens, I'll come and lie down beside you.
Yes!
Okay. Let's eat, shall we?
Mmm. Oh my gosh! It's amazing!
This is the first time I've ever eaten turtle,
but it's delicious.
The turtle is good, but I think the beef is my favorite.
The fresh veggies are pretty tasty, too.
So, basically, everything turned out great!
Yes it did.
I hope Haru'ue gets here before much longer.
Oh, I think she should be arriving any minute now.
I wasn't thinking.
Should we be waiting?
We'll still have plenty of ingredients left
when she gets here.
Oh, yeah. I say we keep eating!
You know, it's a real mystery.
What's a mystery?
Why is it that food always seems to taste better
when it's eaten as a group?
Mm-Hmm. I think cooking it while we eat
like this makes a difference, too.
I guess there's nothing that can beat homemade
when it comes to cookies or stew.
Right, Misaka?
Hey, Sissy, what's the matter?
Are you okay?
Oh. Yeah, I'm fine, really.
Are you sure?
You're panting and sweating, and your face is all red.
Yeah! I said I'm okay!
Oh! These mushrooms look delicious.
That's just adorable.
Oh, you're pure evil, Saten.
Hi, you guys. I'm sorry I'm so late.
Nah, don't worry! Come in, come in!
Oh. Hey, Haru'ue.
Oh, wow! Everything looks delicious!
So, you were able to get your errand taken care of?
Mm-Hmm. I needed to have a talk to my teacher, that's all.
This stew we put together is really good.
Let me get a bowl ready for you, okay?
What's in the bag?
Did you bring something to add, too?
Yeah, I just picked up some noodles.
Ooh! Exactly what we needed.
Sounds great! Throw 'em on in!
Yeah, sure, Sissy, whatever you say!
Oh, come on! I'm telling the truth!
Ah, I am officially full!
I think we may have to diet after this.
That was a lot of fun, huh?
We should really have another study group sometime.
Yeah.
I just wish it didn't require so much paperwork.
Ah! Paperwork?
We're not late, are we?
No, we're still okay.
I do think we might want to
move a little bit faster, though.
If we are so much as a minute past our return time,
the punishment won't be pretty.
Ugh! Let's hurry!
Kuroko? What's wrong? Come on.
Nothing.
Let's go.
Right. I'm with you, Sissy.
There. That should do it.
That didn't take nearly as
long as we thought, huh, Haru'ue?
Yeah. Um, Uiharu?
Yes?
You know. I really am grateful.