I'm home, Mikoto.
What's the matter, dear?
Why are you crying?
Oh, a boo-boo!
Now, now, it'll be all right.
Really?
You just be a good girl, and it
will be fixed up, as good as new.
How's that gonna happen?
Ooh, I know!
Is Santa gonna come and make it all better?
Heh, heh, heh. Santa?
In the middle of spring?
Yep... that's right...
The old fellow is a friend of
mine, so I'll see what I can do.
You know Santa?!
Sure!
Now, close those eyes and get some sleep, okay?
There...
breakfast is served.
Mama!
Look, Mama! All better!
See? Just like you told me!
That's right...
Life was so much simpler as a child...
Whenever something went wrong,
Mama would fix it while I slept.
Like magic.
If only the experiment...
and everything that's happened...
could just be a bad dream...
Something that vanished...
evaporated when I opened my eyes.
Isn't it a beautiful morning, Sissy?!
Oh, I just want a moment to
savor this before getting punched.
Hey... Good morning.
It is a nice day today.
But I haven't been dreaming.
Mama isn't here now to make every little problem go away.
Santa stopped making house calls a long time ago.
And no hero is going to come
dashing to the rescue, either.
Are you going out again today?
Yeah.
Just once more.
Then it should all be over.
Huh?
Today...
Today is the day...
I'm ending this.
It's almost time now.
Sorry, guys.
Maybe someday you'll forgive me...
Maybe someday you'll understand.
Tree Diagram...
The greatest supercomputer in the world.
Loaded aboard the satellite Orihime I
and launched into space by Academy City under the
pretense that it would be analyzing climate data.
Every few weeks, it projects the movement of
all the particles in the Earth's atmosphere,
predicting the weather for the entire month in one go...
The rest of the time, it performs calculations for
all sorts of Academy City-based research projects.
Also...
It is the simulator that's directing the
creation and slaughter of twenty thousand clones.
Hey.
Remedial lessons for you too, huh...?
What class did you fail, Zapper?
Oh, hey... It's you again.
My name's Mikoto Misaka, not Zapper.
I'm really tired, and there are some
things I need to save my strength for today...
So I'm just going to skip the part where I zap you.
Oh, so you can say "zap," but I can't?
Never mind...
Your sister's not with you today?
I just wanted to thank her for helping
me carry all those drinks home yesterday.
Hold on...!
You mean you saw her again?
Uh, yeah... I saw her.
What for?
What do you mean, "what for?"...
I just ran into her, that's all.
Another sun again tomorrow!
Stupid things...
I really can't stand those blimps.
What's wrong with them?
They're nothing but big computers.
Programmed to control us.
For now.
But Tree Diagram's reign is about to end...
I'm destroying that machine.
Uh... Hey!
Today!
What is the deal with that girl?
I mean, jeez!
Is she always so high-strung?
Eh?
Hey, Zapper.
You were just over there, weren't you?
"Since Misaka's name is obviously not Zapper...
I can only assume that you are referring to the cat,"
Misaka tells the rude boy.
Oh, sorry. You're the sister, huh...
Without the goggles, there's no way to tell you two apart.
Oh, by the way... thank you for yesterday.
"Your words of gratitude are noted, but they
were not my objective," replies Misaka honestly.
"I removed the goggles because I needed to feed the cat,
and previous experience has taught me that they are
disturbed by reflective surfaces, such as lenses,"...
Misaka explains her wardrobe change.
Yeah, cats are like that...
So... Why put them back on, then?
"Because it was no longer necessary to
have them off. See?" asks Misaka patiently.
Okay...
so you fed him already?
No, I haven't fed him.
Uh...
then why did you put the goggles back on?
Well?
"The reason behind that action is unimportant,"
Misaka says, refusing to explain.
Huh?
Ah, I get it...
You didn't want anybody seeing your sweet side, did you?
No.
It is not that, exactly.
Fine, I give. What is it?
Hello!
"I refuse to answer that,"
Misaka states, making herself quite clear.
Well... all right, if you say so.
See you later.
"Hold on a moment,"
Misaka says, instructing you to stop walking.
Just tell me what the deal is, will ya?
"You were going to leave...
You were going to abandon this creature.
Walking away from a helpless, hungry cat.
How can you bring yourself to do something so cruel?
Well?"... Misaka asks sternly.
What's with you?
I'm not abandoning him.
You've got food!
"Misaka does have food, but feeding the
cat is nonetheless impossible for her,"
Misaka says, finally relenting.
"Misaka has a critical defect that
prevents her from interacting with the cat,"
Misaka explains further.
A defect?
I'm sure it can't be that bad.
"The descriptor is appropriate...
It's Misaka's body...
It constantly emits a weak magnetic field,"...
Misaka says, explaining her defect.
It is not strong enough for people to detect,
but animals are highly sensitive to it.
Okay, so... let me see if I understand. Animals
tend not to like you because you're a walking magnet?
"It is not that they do not like me.
They simply find it difficult to be around me,"...
Misaka says, correcting your previous statement.
Then give me the food...
I wouldn't mind feeding the ca...
"That is not enough...
Do you not wish to take him in and give him a home?"...
Misaka pointedly inquires.
"If you do not know what happens to animals taken in
by the Health Department, I am happy to inform you.
Well,"... says Misaka, beginning her illustrative tale...
First, the unfortunate creature is placed inside
a polycarbonate case...
Then, twenty milliliters of a
chemical called ASD-10 are injec-
Stop talking!
That is seriously disturbing information...
If you feel so bad, why don't you adopt him.
"Unfortunately, it would not be possible
for Misaka to raise a cat," Misaka answers honestly.
"In addition to the aforementioned critical defect,
Misaka's living space is somewhat unconventional
and thus not conducive to pet ownership,"...
Misaka clearly states her reasons.
Still, I...
Uh...
Okay, okay.
I guess you're coming with me.
You say there's a strange pain in your chest, huh?
I don't see anything that's out of the ordinary.
But Number 10031's turn is coming up tomorrow.
We don't want anything impeding the experiment, do we?
Yeah, you're right...
We should probably look a bit harder.
"No.
It is not something that will affect the experiment,"
says Misaka, offering her own analysis.
Well... since the tests aren't actually showing anything,
your word is good enough for me.
Sorry...
"Suppose you were to encounter a clone of yourself...
What would that experience be like for you?
How would you... feel?" Misaka wishes to know.
A clone of myself?!
Ugh, I don't think I'd like that at all!
Oh, really? But it could be useful.
What...?! Imagine for a second a living
copy of yourself standing in front of you.
Looking like you and talking to you in your own voice!
Just thinking about it makes my insides all squirmy!
Well... when you put it like that,
it does sound kind of creepy.
I can't take it...
You showing up like this...
Looking like you do! Just go away, all right?!
That is how Big Sister feels.
Misaka is creepy, someone she wants nothing to do with.
Hello and welcome to the Academy City Tour Bus...
We are so glad you chose to ride with us today!
We are now entering School District 23,
the area of the city devoted to space exploration.
In this area, as the name suggests,
you will find a variety of facilities
specializing in space technology,
including the Academy City Space Exploration Center,
which boasts its own rocket launch site.
The building you see on the left-hand side
is the data center for the most powerful
supercomputer in the world, Tree Diagram...
This center is a hub for data exchange...
It brings us the city's weather foreca-
It's unusual for a student to be dropping by at this hour.
Sorry... I'm writing a summer break
report and I needed to do some research.
That's very studious of you.
Or it would be, anyway...
if you hadn't waited until the
very last minute to get it done.
Word of advice:
This close to sunset, you want to
avoid going anywhere near the fence.
If you do, the security robots will swarm ya.
Thank you.
I'll be careful.
The data center...
The only point of contact for
communications with Tree Diagram.
From there, I'll hack in and program
it to produce a false prediction.
Like, emergency report:
Have observed a critical error in the
ongoing experiment titled Project Level 6 Shift."
"The error arose as a result of the battle
between test subject Accelerator and Railgun...
The damage done is irreparable...
Consequently, test subject Accelerator
will no longer be able to achieve Level 6."
The researchers, who have put all their eggs in
Tree Diagram's basket, will be thrown into a panic.
Of course, if they order a recalculation,
they'll realize that the error report was inaccurate.
They're bound to catch onto the trick sooner or later...
However...
before they do, I'll drive the
entire project into bankruptcy.
Geez.
You could've saved yourself a lot of pain.
That's my...
Shut up, you moron!
Wait, that's all you have?
Huh?
Hold on.
Black cats are supposedly bad luck, right?
"Why does he keep meowing like that?"
asks Misaka, expressing confusion.
Well, my guess is he's upset because he's still hungry.
So feed him again.
How about you give it a try this time?
I told you... It is impossible for me to feed...
Oh, come on... try.
You see, it worked. He's eating just fine.
Does he appear to be upset now?
No way... He looks pretty happy to me.
Are you happy, cat?
Uh, well... you want to give him a name?
A new name?
But I thought you named him Zapper.
Not Zapper... He's your cat, right?
You should give him a name you like.
Very well.
It's "Dog."
Huh?
Misaka has chosen a name for the
black cat, and that name is Dog.
He is a cat called Dog. Heh.
Come on... honestly...
Can't you think of anything better than that?
You know, something that's a little bit more dignified.
"Okay. King Henry VIII,"
Misaka suggests with a straight face.
Too dignified.
Very well. I will call him "Schrödinger."
Quit messing around! Thought experiment or not,
the man talked about locking a cat in a cage
with some poison and radioactive material.
Obviously not a cat lover!
All right... I shall put it on hold for now.
On hold. Yes?
I see where this is going...
Please don't name him "On Hold," I'm begging you.
Just don't.
"By the way, what is your current destination?
This is a different route than the one we took
yesterday with the beverages," Misaka observes accurately.
A little detour...
There's a book that I need to pick up.
"Do you wish to go to the shopping district, then?"
Misaka asks and then points out...
"Geographically speaking,
making a right turn at the previous
intersection would be the shorter route."
Nope... that's not it.
I'm headed for a used book store past there.
I don't imagine raising a cat
has changed much over the years.
"You are going to the store to find a
book on how to properly care for a cat,"
says Misaka, seeking confirmation.
Yeah, I'd say that about sums it up.
If it was just me, I'd be fine,
but you were at my place, right?
You saw the nun's habit and the priestess's robes...
It's for those two.
"In other words, you intend to shirk your responsibility
and foist caring for the cat onto somebody else."...
Misaka says, clarifying.
No, that isn't what I'm saying at all.
What's wrong... Are you angry?
"No, I am not angry...
However, if you fail to treat the
cat with adequate care and concern...
I will have you charged with destruction of property,"
states Misaka as a serious warning.
I knew it. You are angry.
No, I am not angry.
Well, I'm gonna go in and see what I can find...
You wait out here for me.
"I understand,"...
Misaka acknowledges the instruction.
There was a hidden meaning in there, I know it.
Oh... now that I think about it...
I probably shouldn't go into the store carrying a cat.
I do not mean to sound as if
I am lecturing you about this,
but please do not give him to me, as I cannot hold...
Here, catch! Kitty Bomb!
Your magnetic field freaks him out...
but if you can get past that barrier,
that'll be a sign of a real bond between you!
"Horrible boy...
Does he think he can get away with that?
One simply does not use a kitten to play catch."
Misaka says, talking to herself under her breath.
Is that an upset meow?
Or a happy one?
How do I tell them apart?
We were out of line. We're sorry man.
We get the message. You don't need to...
Oh, come on...
You were the ones who started it in the first place.
You don't really think you're going
to get off with an apology, do you?
It hurts! It hurts...! It hurts!
Please, just stop! Ahh!
Pathetic...
I know about ten thousand girls who can take
much worse than that without so much as a whimper.
No, please!
Hey, help a guy out.
I gotta work up an appetite for dinner somehow.
Yeah... I guess it is about that time again, isn't it?
Lucky you. It looks like you get to live for another day.
Thank you for waiting.
"I hope I have not kept you long...
I am Misaka 10031, your next opponent," Misaka reports.
Tch... okay...
You guys get kinda' confusing after awhile.
"Should I apologize for your confusion?" asks Misaka.
I don't need an apology from
somebody who'll be dead before tomorrow.
Operation confirmed.
Misakas 10031 and 10032 will proceed
with the predetermined course of action.
This is strange...
There isn't a hint of anyone here.
If the sensors weren't working,
the cameras probably aren't, either.
This facility is the end-all be-all,
the point of communication with Academy City's brain.
But here I am.
Moving around unimpeded after getting past
their meager display of exterior security.
Have they fled?
Is this a trap?
Whatever the case, there should be more to it than this.
How do they benefit from letting me get this far in?
Are they just that sure that
hacking into the system is impossible?
Even the control room is deserted.
The facility appears to be functioning...
But...
This didn't just happen...
The utter emptiness, the layer of dust coating everything.
This place has been abandoned for a while.
But why?
This is nothing like what I expected.
I'll do what I came here for and...
Is this it?
What does that mean?
Number of transmissions today: 0...?
There should be several hundred
requests to Tree Diagram each day.
No... the requests are here.
They just haven't been processed...
Nor were yesterday's, or the day before...
These are reports.
A bunch of them...
23rd Report... 24th Report...
What does that say?!
"This is the final report regarding
the disappearance of Tree Diagram."
"On June 28 at zero zero twenty hours,
all communications ceased and Tree
Diagram disappeared from its satellite track.
That same day, at zero one fifteen,
Search Party 1 was dispatched."
"Later, at zero three forty,
one section of Tree Diagram's remnants was recovered...
Analysis indicates that Tree Diagram was...
Tree Diagram...
no longer exists.
Then...
Let's see here...
Cat book... cat book... cat book...
Tree Diagram doesn't exist.
The experiments continue.
There must be something I can do to save them!
"Misaka must go on to the next experiment," says Misaka...
Stop... Please!