Confirm.
It's three minutes past the rendezvous time.
This is Point A.
Confirmed, there's no one in sight yet.
All right... So they're no-shows.
Guess they realized they were
messing with the wrong people.
Now you're just being ridiculous.
Hey! Who was that?
I'm here, as we agreed...
Closer than you know, in fact.
The deal is off... It's off.
Get out of there right now!
Who are you?
Heh.
Ahh!
You! Stay back!
What's that? Again?
Yeah... Yeah, all right...
Fine. So who is it?
Pharmaceuticals? Really?
Isn't that a little...
Sure, that's true. It's not like
I don't see what you're saying...
but, all told...
the whole point of a swimsuit is to
show off your body to other people...
so going to a private pool defeats the
purpose of wearing one, if you see what I mean.
Okay.
But all of the public pools and
beaches are always ultra crowded...
There's no room, so it's next to impossible to swim.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
I hadn't thought about that.
What do you think, Takitsubo?
Hmm...
As long there's space to just float
like a corpse, it doesn't matter to me.
Oh... Okay...
Ladies, let's cut the chit chat while we're working.
Kinuhata, that's enough...
We've got a new request, so we're heading back.
What time?
Good question. The request is somewhat vague.
Huh?
That said...
our task sounds like it'll be simple enough.
Hey... I don't know how much I like
taking on a job that's so vague...
But, all told, Mugino, you're the boss, so whatever.
So, what is the job?
Protecting a facility from a mysterious invader...
The pay isn't too bad, either...
I think this is perfect.
Just the kind of job we here at ITEM like to take on.
An esper with the power to control electricity, huh?
The attacks have been conducted
via communications lines,
and no intruder has been caught by electronic security,
so that's their guess.
Actually... the client seems to have
this rather narrowly profiled already.
So they've got a suspect in mind?
In that case, why don't they
set up their own counterattack?
I think that it would be ultra easy to stage an ambush.
You are only to act once the
target is within the facility...
and you are not to pry into the particulars...
those are the client's orders.
Uh? What's with these guys?
I don't like how this job is going so far.
What do you want?
A job's a job.
We don't take them because they're fun...
Anyway... they sought you out for this gig...
I'm sure they had their reasons...
Now quit your whining and get to work!
Okay.
So that's the job...
just lie in wait then take out the opponent?
Basically.
With one catch, though...
There are two facilities that our
mystery attacker could potentially target.
Ooh! I can cover one of them by myself!
Huh?
What's with you?
I thought you didn't like this job.
Liking the job has nothing to do with it...
I mean if I'm the one to take 'em out,
then I earn the kill shot bonus, don't I?
All right, Frenda...
Just make sure you stay in contact.
Don't get in over your head, okay?
Only two places left.
Including this one.
At this point, I don't know how
far they've gone with the experiment.
And I don't think I want to know.
But either way.
It ends tonight.
I volunteered for this 'cause the pay was so enticing...
but waiting around for somebody who may
not even show up certainly is boring...
All told, this really sucks.
And if they go to the other facility
while I'm stuck here waiting at this one...
then all these tedious minutes of
utter boredom will have been for nothing!
No way!
The target's actually here!
Well, I'm ready...
Time to earn that kill shot bonus.
All right.
The research facility I'm after is on the top floor.
If I get lucky...
maybe I can pull this off without a hitch.
Of course not.
Like it would ever actually be that easy.
Not a single one hit her?
Did she use magnetism to divert the stone's path?
It looks like the Intel about
an electrical esper was right.
There we go...
Ordinarily, this is a tool used
to burn through walls and doors,
but tonight...
A bomb?
What kind of scientists are these?
Putting bombs inside of stuffed animals?
They're igniting the bombs using fuses
they set up in the room ahead of time...
I don't get it.
Why would they want to make this such a big production?
Wha...? A bomb in the rubble?
They're predicting my moves.
Does that mean they know they're
being attacked by an Electromaster?
I was hoping not to use my maximum magnetism...
It does a lot of damage.
Never mind that... Where are they?
More of those fuses?
Maybe if I follow where they lead...
She's the one, huh?
Are you sure?
Yes... I heard it was pathological analysis.
Word is they're the ones who got hit.
What a relief.
That should buy us some time...
Still, we need to hurry up with our move.
Excuse me...
What is it?
Well, uh...
There's a visitor.
Hello.
I'm sorry if I've kept you waiting...
It's nice to meet you...
Uh... please forgive me, but you are?
I'm the one who was in charge of
your company's Testament oversight.
My name's Nunotaba.
Almost!
That stupid girder is in my way.
I don't want any more interference later on.
I'll deal with her now.
She's put up quite a fight so far...
Chances are if I'd used my
remote-control bombs, she'd be dead by now.
But with an Electromaster of her level, it's
possible she could've taken control of them, instead.
All told... it was the right decision.
And... boom!
No way!
She can deflect ceramic bombs?
She's on an entirely different level
than any other esper I've gone up against.
You won't get away...
I don't know if you're directly
involved or just a hired goon.
But anyone who supports this experiment...
...will pay!
Oh, dear! I'm terrified!
Just look at her!
If she catches me, she'll tear me into tiny little pieces!
Heh. Yeah, as if!
I lured her up as high as I could,
so that was quite a fall she took.
It doesn't matter how high-level an esper you are after...
...that?
No. That's impossible.
If you were wanting to see me fall, you
should've fought me in a different building.
One that wasn't built using any steel, for example.
You should be gone! No fair!
Aww!
Looks like you've hit a dead end.
It does, huh?
I never expected to be backed into a corner like this.
It happens.
It is a pretty easy mistake to make...
Perhaps you were panicking and
took a wrong turn somewhere...
Or maybe...
Heh.
What do you think?
Oh, I'm sorry if it wasn't clear...
There isn't really anything specific we need from you.
It's just, this is the first time
we've done a large-scale move like this...
so I thought, you know, if anything were to happen...
it would be good to have you around...
given your previous involvement with the project.
Of course. I understand.
Thank you, I thought that you might...
Well, then, if you'll excuse me for a moment.
There's something I want to ask you, while I still can.
It's a simple question... Who hired you?
Huh?
Now isn't the time to be concerned about loyalty...
This facility is part of a cruel experiment...
Yeah, yeah, never mind about all that.
My employer's background, their objectives, the
morality of the person I've been hired to eliminate...
the possibility that they're fighting for a noble cause...
All told, those sorts of things...
Just don't really matter to me.
Do you understand your situation now?
Let me explain something to you,
you've heard those stories before, right?
The ones about the hunter becoming the hunted.
Take a look at where you're standing.
Your retreat is cut off.
There's nothing to shield your self with...
Now what will you do?
Go ahead. I'd love to see you get out of this one!
Heh.
Well, so much for that...
You try to end things in a
civilized way, and look what happens.
My work's not over.
I need to save as much of my strength as I can.
She actually lifted up the floor!
Oh no... Does that mean...
Am I fighting a Level 5 esper?
I'm done with you!
Then again, people with too much
power do have a tendency to be careless.
Uh-oh!
That's what you get for making your next move so obvious.
A stun grenade!
Serves me right... I got sloppy.
I love seeing a cocky, powerful esper
like that trapped by my own hands...
It makes me feel all warm and fuzzy inside!
All told, messing with me can be hazardous to your health!
All right! That's half the paycheck!
Half the money for this gig goes to me!
Money for me! Money for me!
I'm so excited! I wonder what I should buy...
She's gone?
That wasn't enough firepower to incinerate her.
So... I guess...
if she's not there, she must be...
I'll give you this much, at least.
You've done your homework on Electromasters.
But I'm at a slightly higher level...
EM waves provide me with a
picture of the surrounding space.
Whoa, there!
Best not to make any sudden moves.
I'm starting to get my sight and my hearing back...
And at such a close range, nothing
can outrun my electric shocks.
Uh... Mijihi!
Huh?
Miji... cavi... Capri...
Huh? What is she saying?
I've never heard a language like that...
Hold on... one of those words could have been...
It's gibberish... Gotcha!
Hah!
Another bomb?
When will she give up?
What is that?
Academy City's specially-made gaseous explosive.
They call it Ignus.
It won't do you any harm to breathe it in...
but then, it's an explosive, not a poison.
The way it's filling the air now...
It's turning this room into one big bomb.
So...
do you know what would happen if you used electricity?
Well... I think I'll kill you now nice... and slow!
Not good.
Electricity is out of the question, and using
magnetism runs the risk of creating friction.
Ah!
Is this girl a psycho?
It's not impossible that all the stomping
around she's doing could kick up a spark.
I can tell you're wondering if I have a death wish.
In case you haven't noticed, I work for the underworld.
You think I can do that and still be afraid of dying?
Yeah, right!
I couldn't be more full of it!
There's no way I'm dying in here with you.
The canister I tossed first
was the real thing, all right...
but what I dispersed afterward was just ordinary nitrogen.
I didn't think she would fall
for it so completely, though.
So, what's the deal with the underworld
cleaner they've got standing by?
Oh, nothing much...
I don't know what she can do,
really. She's only a little girl.
Never mind her.
I wonder what's happening at the other facility.
Who knows?
Any means of external communication have been disabled.
I just want to hurry and get this move over with.
But if something were to go wrong.
Well, that's why we called in a patsy, right?
So somebody else can take the responsibility.
Yeah, there is that.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Nunotaba...
Where is she?
Restroom, maybe?
Moving the Sisters that are being
adjusted would normally come last.
With the abrupt transfer of control
and the watch out for attackers,
they've ignored internal security.
If I'm really going to do this...
it's now or never.
You're hanging in there pretty well.
But if I don't finish you off pretty
soon, Mugino and the others will show up,
and I don't like to share with others.
I told you before that I don't
care much about my targets' lives...
I do care about their deaths, however,
and I'm especially interested in yours.
When I take a life...
it's an exquisite feeling.
Because in that moment, I am in complete
control of someone else's destiny...
It feels great... that power...
As if the only reason that person was
born... was to have their life ended by me.
Now, enough talk.
All told, I just want to hear
one good, final scream from you.
To be born for the sole reason of being murdered...
To accept that...
to take life for granted...
never trying to escape...
or attempting to fight it...
never seeking to be saved...
from such a godforsaken destiny...
I say to hell with that!
Oh no.
A choke hold...
Shocks aren't her only line of defense.
Can't breathe!
Not a bad idea. You almost had me, but...
Huh?
That was a really close call...
I can't believe I almost blew half
my body off with my own explosives!
Just imagine...
My beautiful legs would have been...
Okay, I see...
so that's how it is...
It was a trick...
You didn't fill the room with explosive gas, did you?
All told, I fell for a simple bluff.
Well... uh... I...
Man... "I said "All told,"
You're rubbing off on me...
Tee-hee!
You seem like a pretty terrible person to me...
I'm not gonna lose any sleep if I shock you to death...
Just thought you should know.
I want all the info you have on the project...
I mean every last detail.
Who's the one in charge?
Who hired you to do this?
Yeah, Too bad I don't know that,
since we go through an intermediary.
Oh, I forgot...
You said somebody else was on the way here, didn't you?
Who?
There's no way I'm telling you that.
You've got three seconds to answer me...
unless you want to be burned to a cinder.
Three...
No! No! I'll talk! I'll talk!
Two...
My tongue! That last shock must have...
Wait! Hold on! My tongue is too numb to talk! Honestly!
Please don't kill me!
One...
Zero.
Huh?
I see.
So you're not going to sell out your friends, huh?
No... I would, I just can't talk.
All right... I can't hold that against you.
It got quiet in here all of a sudden.
I was sure the Electromaster had finished you off.
Looks like I got here just in time.
Hello, Frenda.
Mikoto Misaka...
I'm putting an end to this.
I can't let her take them on without any help at all.
I'll save the rest of them!
Yes... I'll do what I can...
I'll help her.