"How to shift experiment subject Accelerator to Level 6."
"Out of Academy City's seven Level 5 espers, it has
been determined that only Accelerator can reach Level 6.
"Project Radio Noise."
"Since that number of Railguns cannot be
produced, a different plan has been developed.
"Sissy" sounds more like a nickname for an upperclassman.
"We are her sisters," says Misaka in conclusion.
10032... Date: August the 21st. Time: Twenty-thirty hours.
A dangerous, intrusive person who likes to
do room inspections without prior warning.
A guy like this I can already tell.
A visitor to the dorms? That's unusual.
A way to force them to stop.
About all of your Sisters.
After all that.
After killing 20,000 Sisters in various
scenarios, Accelerator will achieve... Level 6.
After that number of victories,
All that is wishful thinking.
And it was all totally legal of course.
And now you know everything.
And that makes it my duty
And you're convinced that, if you die
And, if this plan fails them, too...
Answer me.
Anyway, what business do you have
with Sissy that brings you here so late?
Are you saying you have some other solution to offer?
Are you some kind of pervert?
As far as he knows,
At 02:23 on August the 20th. Test 10030.
Before it begins, I'm going to track down Accelerator
and fight him with every ounce of strength in my body.
Besides, when curfew hits, the
dorm security will be activated,
But I do know I can't afford to lose to you today!
But I'm not gonna let you just march off to your death.
But earlier today you said all
of this would be over for good.
But, if I was to be unceremoniously beaten on the
very first move, lying there, helpless and pathetic.
But, the way you've got it planned.
Calm down! It's all right.
Can you defeat him?
Come in.
Cut the crap.
Damn it!
Did you come to tell me how disgusted you are with me?
Do things your way, and you won't save anybody.
Do you know what Tree Diagram predicts?
Do you really think they'll be grateful to you?
Do you think I'm going to stand aside
just because you put your hands up?
Do you understand now?
Don't do this!
Don't just stand there calmly while you ruin all my plans!
Don't just stand there. Come into
the room, and close the door please.
Don't you see?
Even if he does know something,
Even if it isn't the truth.
Everyone has their own secret, special habits.
Evil and disgusting.
Fight me!
For her sake.
For instance.
From next door, maybe?
Get down there!
Good boy.
He is not going to approve of my plan.
He may not have all the facts,
but the outcome's the same, anyway.
He must have been captivated by
Sissy's beauty and followed her back here!
He'd kill you for sure!
He's probably come here to condemn me.
He's the troglodyte I saw with
Sissy by the vending machine!
Heh.
Hello? Are you there?
Here we go again.
Here, kitty.
Hey! Did you hear that? It sounds like a patrol!
Hey, you know, if you guys share a room,
Hm...
Hold on, Railgun?
Honestly.
How about this.
How can you smile like that
after everything that's happened?
How could they do it?
How could they?
How many times have I tried to fry you now?
However the Misaka who died today was serial number 10031.
However, I am expecting her at any moment now.
However, what if I'm even worse than they expect me to be?
Huh?
Huh? I don't get it.
Huh? What are you doing on somebody else's bed?
I already said.
I apologize.
I blame myself.
I can do whatever I want, whenever I want.
I can't drag anybody else into this mess with me!
I can't take any other route than this.
I cannot just continue to ignore this.
I could actually make myself useful.
I didn't get to ask him anything.
I do not have time for this stupid charade!
I don't get it!
I don't have time for this.
I don't know if I have any chance of beating him,
I don't think I could do that. Not without her permission.
I guess I have the wrong room, I'm sorry!
I have already resolved not to
act on any information I may acquire.
I have the file.
I have to send you outside until she's gone.
I heard some unusual noises.
I know that face.
I know you have your own goals.
I know you've convinced yourself
you're doing the right thing here.
I know. I heard them, too.
I let him slide before because I thought he would be
a good example for Sissy of how useless boys truly are,
I live here with her. I'm Sissy's roommate.
I mean what I say!
I must stop this right now! If I breathe
in her scent for too long, I'll pass out.
I read all about the project.
I really can't stand those blimps.
I really hate this!
I refuse to fight you.
I saw to it that her previous roommate was reassigned
I take it Misaka's not home.
I think your heart may even
have stopped for a second there.
I told myself I was going to wait.
I told myself I would wait.
I was just thinking, "I'm glad I'm on her side."
I wish there was some way to know what I should do!
I won't fight you!
I won't fight.
I would hate for these mysterious noises to disturb her.
I'll do it. I will hurt you.
I'll fight him.
I'll stop the experiment and bring your sister back.
I'm a participant in the
experiment who volunteered her DNA.
I'm afraid it does not offer much in
the way of entertainment for guests.
I'm going to do whatever I have to, to stop this!
I'm here 'cause I'm concerned.
I'm not bluffing. I'll fry the
life out of you if I have to!
I'm not going to fight you.
I'm not moving.
I'm still not sure what kind of power you used against me.
I'm trying to put a stop to them!
I've got an idea.
I've never been able to land an
attack on him like that before.
If I die tonight.
If my one life can save ten thousand of theirs,
If the head resident finds you here in this
room, it's going to mean big trouble for both of us!
If you don't want to fight,
then get the hell out of my way!
If you have something pressing to discuss
with her, I recommend you come in and wait.
If you want to stop me, then fight like a man!
If you're not going to move, I'll
happily shoot right through you.
If, for example, I lost the fight after the first move.
Impossible! He knows!
In fact, I'm actually a full year behind her.
Is Misaka there? This is Kamijo.
Is this stupid thing even working?
It didn't feel like it was negated like the other times.
It doesn't really matter what I try against
him, There's no way that I can win in a fair fight.
It felt like it went through him.
It is the truth.
It would be best if you avoided
raising your voice so loudly.
It's a cat.
It's her!
It's my fault.
It's not like some hero is going
to come dashing to the rescue.
It's not much, but maybe it's enough?
It's starting soon. I have to hurry.
Just a moment!
Just let me go.
Just standing.
Just who are you, anyway?
Just-Just a minute!
Let's say he was handily
defeated in a fight with a Level 0.
Like rats or guinea pigs.
Like you never secretly pressed
your lips to your crush's picture.
Mama isn't here now to make every little problem go away.
Maybe the researchers would see that
and begin to doubt the whole project.
Maybe they'd be forced to reconsider the simulations.
Maybe we'll both win.
Maybe you live in a world that's
full of happy endings for everybody!
Mine is seeing everybody get through this alive.
Misaka's asleep already?
No way.
No!
No, I haven't!
No, no, you are not mistaken.
No... I made up my mind.
Normally I'd kill someone for that.
Not only that, but you looked inside of my stuffed bear.
Nothing in there, either.
Now here I am.
Now take your idealism and stuff it.
Now, come on.
Of all places.
Oh, okay. Hello then.
Oh, really?
Oh, well.
Oh, whoops.
Oh. are you sure?
On August the 21st. Test 10031.
On second thought, you need not tell me.
On the other hand!
Ow! Hey! Cut it out!
Perhaps I can help you find what's causing them?
Perhaps the next floor up?
Please let me!
Please, help.
Programmed to control us.
Put the claws away!
Really it's not even a difficult decision to make.
Really, go ahead. The door is not locked.
Regardless of what Sissy might say.
Santa stopped making house calls a long time ago.
Say what you want. I'm not moving.
Say you die and your Sisters all survive.
Saying nice things, trying to reassure me.
She knew about this.
She knew.
She knows about the existence of the clones.
She's catching up on her rest now.
She's in goodness knows how much trouble, and he
thinks he can just casually make an appearance like this!
She's not.
Shh!
Shut up, you fool.
Sissy.
So I...
So like I said, let's cut the crap.
So please, just go.
So that's it.
So you better be ready to fight for your life
So, by losing to him.
So, let's work together.
So, why are you here?
So, will you step aside?
So, you want to settle this by force, do you?
So, your name's Kamijo?
Somebody, help.
Stop crying.
Stupid monkey!
Stupid things.
Surely there's only one thing they could think.
That is odd, isn't it?
That means ten thousand Sisters get to live.
That one there's actually my bed.
That paper. How did you?
That something must've been wrong with Tree
Diagram's original programming. They'll stop.
That would be the best idea
if you do not wish to miss her.
That you'll be dead in 185 moves.
That's Zapper, isn't it?
That's a promise, okay?
That's impossible!
That's really creepy.
That's right.
That's too bad. Do it anyway!
That's what they refer to themselves as.
That's what you think?
The 7th Pharmaceutical Research Center.
The Tree Diagram satellite was actually attacked
from the ground and brought down a few weeks back.
The cost has already been too great!
The experiment's based on the supposition
that Accelerator's the strongest esper.
The experiment's basic premise would be flawed.
The experiments and everything.
The experiments.
The look on her face.
The optimal plan would involve creating one
hundred and twenty-eight different battlefields
The pathological analysis lab.
The prediction that I'd lose after
185 moves would be proved wrong.
The very fact that you're holding that file means
Their bodies are messed around
with for the sake of research.
Then why are...
Then you have no reason to worry.
Then...
There is no telling how long you'll be waiting for her.
There is the possibility that he
might know something about Sissy!
There isn't any wind.
There may well be something I
can do to help the situation.
There was something there.
There won't be any recalculations.
There's another experiment being held tonight.
There's no choice.
There's no room!
There's only one more thing I can think of to try.
They aren't stupid.
They compare themselves to laboratory
animals without so much as batting an eye.
They know exactly what it means
to be some scientist's lab rat.
They know, and still...
They may seem strange to other people, but
that doesn't make them wrong or perverted at all.
They wouldn't be able to.
They're in this situation because of me.
They're nothing but big computers.
Things will turn ugly if anybody outside hears you.
Think about it.
This doesn't have anything to do with you.
This is room 208, or is it?
This is something I have to do on my own!
This is the last time I'm gonna say it.
This isn't getting us anywhere. What, are you so
heartless you think since they're just a bunch of clones,
This plan involves the mass production of 'Sisters.'"
This room is primarily intended for sleeping in.
This whole project!
Uh, no thank you.
Uh, oh, right.
Uh-huh.
Uhh...
Um, maybe I should...
Um, yeah, hi.
Unless you want that, step aside!
Wait, what's Level 6? I've never heard of it.
We have no time!
We're talking about a guy so strong and arrogant
Well go ahead, then.
Well sure. She is older than I am.
Well then.
Well, I promise I don't deserve it.
Well, here's the thing.
Well, sorry, in a world like
that, there's no place for me!
Well, well, well.
Well, what if he's proven to be incredibly weak?
What are you saying?
What do you think you're doing?
What is going on with you?
What they're doing is crazy.
What're you?
What's it to you?
What's the deal with you tonight? I'm just...
What's wrong with them?
What, did he climb out? This isn't a jungle!
What?
Where are you going now?
Who's that?
Why are you doing this?
Why did it turn out like this?
Why isn't my power working?
Why shouldn't there be somebody else blaming me, too?
Why would you put yourself through this?
Work with me.
Wouldn't they just do some
recalculations and start back up again?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah. As far as the researchers are concerned.
Tree Diagram's projections are absolute.
Yeah. I know they're wrong.
Yes, she is.
Yes?
You are going to die tonight.
You came here looking for Sissy, correct?
You can fight, but do you really think you'll win?
You can open it from out there.
You can stop playing the noble idiot now!
You could be a detective.
You could easily have turned a blind
eye and pretended that you knew nothing.
You could have just continued living your normal life.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You don't mean...
You just have to hide underneath the bed!
You know these experiments are wrong, don't you?
You know what the Sisters say?
You know what?
You know, it's kinda nice to hear someone say that.
You look like hell.
You might as well have a seat over on the bed.
You must have realized it.
You only met my clone yesterday, and you already
got your hands on this top-secret information.
You plan to die.
You see, lately she hasn't been sleeping well at night.
You're an idiot.
You're here at an all-girls
dorm and you call me a pervert?
You're not coming home tonight, are you, Sissy?
You're out here, too. So why don't you
just mind your own business and leave me...
You're really a complete idiot, aren't you?
You're right.
and then I took her place.
and when they're used up, that's that.
and you will no longer be able to wait in the lobby.
because if you don't, you will die!
but I have to try. For their sake.
but this situation is swiftly becoming unacceptable!
doesn't that make the two of you classmates?
he wouldn't even break a sweat if he
had to defend himself from an entire army!
it is believed that Accelerator would advance to Level 6."
it's no big deal if they die?
or stole the seat from her bicycle to caress.
that's a good thing isn't it?
the entire project will come crashing to a halt?
to make sure the ones who are left survive.
upon which Railgun would be killed.
won't move.
you've been in my room without my permission.
you've got it all planned out, huh?