So, like I was saying...
Good morning!
Eh?
Oh, hey. It's Misaka...
Um... You got here pretty quickly, huh?
Huh? Quickly? No... Same time as normal.
Really? But we just saw you in town.
Yeah, it was definitely you, and you were
walking in the opposite direction from the school.
Oh... well, that's impossible, isn't it?
You must've seen someone who looks like me.
Clones? That's crazy!
I mean it!
There's a story that's been going around
about a project designed to clone Level 5 espers.
You haven't heard of it?
No, I haven't.
Sounds pretty amazing though?
Really? The rumors get dumber every day.
Seriously!
You mean they're mass-producing them to use as weapons!
Oh, yeah, it'll be common practice soon.
No way!
Absolutely!
That's ridiculous.
Think about it:
there are only seven Level 5s in Academy City, right?
So, which of them are they cloning?
Oh, come on!
Well... That's just the thing.
I heard who they might be using.
The Level 5 is supposedly that Railgun girl.
So, it's you...
The Original.
Original? Sorry?
You must at least have heard the rumors, right?
What rumors?
Hmph... I have to say, I'm surprised.
I guess the students at Nagatenjoki
like gossip as much as anyone, huh?
So... that's all?
You've heard some rumors, but
do you actually know anything...
You are still a middle-schooler.
But I am a high-schooler...
And you will observe my seniority...
Basically... Watch your tone with me.
I... I was just wondering if you had
any more substantial information about it.
More than you do...
Although, from what I can tell...
Their methods and objectives have
changed considerably since I was there.
Knowing more would only hurt you.
What's the point when there's
nothing you can do about it, anyway?
I asked you for information, not for protection...
And what do you mean I can't do anything?
Are you saying there's something that you can...
Is there, maybe, something that you can do?
I have taken some action already.
Distributing those Money Cards was part of the plan.
The plan to eliminate this city's blind spots.
Placing the Money Cards all over directs
people's attention to the alleys and back streets
that the surveillance cameras don't reach.
By doing so, I hoped I could put an end to the
experiments that have been taking place in the shadows.
Of course...
I was careless enough to let myself be spotted
by those thugs and they followed me back here.
If they had seen this,
it could have created some serious problems for me...
As always...
Leaving physical evidence isn't smart.
I'm not legitimately renting this place, either.
It would be best if we got
out of here before they woke up.
Hold on a second!
I mean... Please tell me...
What are you even talking about?
And who exactly are you?
Now you're thinking...
"As long as I'm destroying physical evidence,
shouldn't I get rid of the witnesses, too?"
Whoa, I am not!
Come on, we need to get these guys...
Not my problem.
Eh?!
What's going on? Is it a fire?
Yeah, a small one...
Doesn't look like anyone was hurt, though.
Man! Who was that psycho?
She actually got two good hits on me...
and said nothing I understood.
Why am I taking anything she said seriously?
That's it! I'm just wasting my time...
I'm going to head home, have a
nice shower... and hit the sack.
It's ridiculous...
I don't care how many people said it, it isn't true...
There's just no way...
There are no clones of me.
Although...
As you can see, the model DNA information is
absolutely indispensable to cloning technology...
It's true...
I did give someone my DNA map once...
but that was a long time ago...
and it was for a different reason...
I'm sure he put it to good use.
Besides... not long afterwards...
that hospital was closed down for good... and now...
She goes to Nagatenjoki Academy.
I can hack into the student records...
Academy City's public telephone
net terminal security is Rank D.
The data terminals used by
school faculty members are Rank B.
However... if I just use my ability...
Right there!
"Shinobu, Nunotaba...
Third year of high school... Age seventeen."
Has distinguished herself in the field of
biological psychiatry from a young age...
Worked with Yamashita University Hospital
Network and Higuchi Pharmaceuticals..."
Eh?! Hold on! Yamashita?!
She was really there then?
So she might actually know something...
"...and Higuchi Pharmaceuticals, collaborating
on a project at the Seventh Research Center...
She later re-enrolled in school."
So is that the place where they've got my DNA map?
Knowing more would only hurt you.
What's the point when there's
nothing you can do about it, anyway?
Asking her for more answers won't do any good.
She'll just keep evading the question.
All right!
I guess I'll have to sneak into this place!
Going in my uniform would be a bad idea.
I'll take this along with it, please.
'Kay... Oh, yes.
I can tell these will look adorable on you!
Cash or card?
Oh... I'll pay with cash, thanks.
Got the clothes.
And now I need to find somewhere
I can go to change into them.
Unfortunately, all of our single rooms are occupied.
We do have some doubles...
All right... I'll take one of those, please.
This room's kind of a waste just for changing my clothes.
Well... Here goes.
Wow, those are all yours?
Pretty impressive, huh?
Well, to be honest, Misaka did help me find them...
Now... I know there are a lot
of people looking for them...
but finding this many in a single day has to be a record!
When you add them all up, it's quite a tidy sum.
Really? Then I wonder if that means I'm rich, too.
You... you found these? All of them?
Before term started, I wanted to
familiarize myself with the area.
I collected these while I was exploring.
Hey, I'm home! Sorry I'm so late.
Thanks for doing this, Saten...
You know how things can be when we've got a new case...
Uh... are you okay?
I've been beaten.
Uh... I'm sorry...
Anyway, I hope you're all hungry
because I bought all of us a supper!
Ooh, I'm starving!
Mmm... it smells delicious!
Yeah.
It doesn't sound so good to me.
I like this stuff as much as the next person...
But maybe you could've gotten something cold instead?
Really?
I actually think it was a perfect choice...
Hot meals taste even better in hot weather!
It's so good!
You've converted her.
Wow, these are delicious, Haru'ue!
You think so?
Mm-hmm. Oh, that's right... I forgot.
You've taken up cooking lately, haven't you?
Oh, yeah?
Uh... Well... I'm still learning.
Really?
As far as I'm concerned, this is just about perfect!
You know my secret?
I add a little bit of soy sauce
and oyster sauce to the mix.
It's absolutely fantastic!
Mmm-hmm...
I think it's exactly what this meal needed!
It complements the strawberries' sweetness, huh?
It sure does!
I just realized I used up the rice.
We don't have any for tomorrow.
That's okay...
I'm sure we can make do without it...
Although... It would be nice if we
had a larger rice cooker, wouldn't it?
You two do eat a lot of the stuff, huh?
Do... Do we, really?
Oh... by the way, Saten...
I was wondering, what did you mean
by what you said on the phone earlier?
Huh? About what?
The stuff you were saying about Misaka...
Something about a mistaken identity?
Oh, that. It was no big deal, really...
I just thought I saw somebody
who looked like her that's all...
Although...
Oh... never mind...
They say everybody in the world
has a look-alike out there somewhere.
I probably just thought it was her
because she was wearing a Tokiwadai Uniform.
Now that you mention it...
Misaka and Shirai always seem
to be wearing their uniforms.
Tokiwadai requires students to wear
uniforms at all times, even outside of school.
That's pretty strict.
I can see why you might think that...
but those uniforms are constant
proof that they are young ladies.
I have a hard time imagining Misaka
wearing anything but her uniform.
Oh, yeah?
Okay, but still...
It would be nice to see them in
street clothes sometimes, you know?
Okay... well...
Alright! Here I go!
That was a close one...
She seemed bound and determined
to find someone to punish tonight.
Still not back.
It's long past curfew now. What are you doing out there?
Oh, Sissy!!
Oh, how improper of me. I should be ashamed of myself!
But then... It has been a really long time!
Siiissssy!!
What the... What was that? I just
got a creepy chill down my spine.
Oh, well... It's gone now.
Transform! Magical Powered Kanam...
Huh?
Hey, what's going on with this thing?
I just bought it... Stupid piece of junk.
Okay! Are you ready!
Oh, that did it.
Ugh! I lost again?
Hah! You get to make the rounds now.
Yeah, I know... Don't rub it in.
I still don't see why we have to do rounds...
This place has airtight security.
Yeah, yeah.
Quit your griping already and get to it.
I'm goin'!
Security cameras, infrared sensors, and electronic locks.
They've got it all...
But, since everything depends
on electricity, I should be fine.
I just have to make sure to keep an eye
out for guards and any other late-night staff.
Hmm? That doesn't make sense...
No departments match what I'm looking for.
Wait... There is a section that has
power but is disconnected from the network.
I was wondering why they only put
surveillance cameras in the hallways.
But I guess it's because they don't want other
departments to know what they're researching.
All right...
I think I'll start by checking that section.
Who's there?
I... I'm not imagining things am I?
Is someone there? Show yourself!
Uh-oh...
What do I do?
Worst case, I guess I could always
shock him unconscious and get myself out...
But I'd really rather not leave any trace that I was here.
Let me think...
What's this?
A security robot! Of course it is...
There's no way anyone could get in here.
Anything to report?
No abnormalities have been detected.
No, huh?
Keep it up.
Good enough for me. I'll just skip the rest of the patrol.
Huh? The alarm?
How come?
The sensors shouldn't be able to pick me up!
Did I miss something?
Keep calm...
Well, for now, at least...
Whoa! What's wrong with you?
Hey! Come back!
What now?
Give up for tonight and get out of here? No.
It doesn't appear to be me they found...
and all this confusion could be my chance...
All right... Keep going!
Hey! What the hell is going on?
Sorry, man!
I totally forgot to tell you...
It's too loud! I can't hear you! Just turn it off!
It finally stopped. Who's there?!
Alright, let's see what they're hiding.
What are those?
Incubators? Each big enough to hold a person.
Can I help you with something?
What are you doing? You aren't lost, are you?
How exactly did you get in here?
Oh... Never mind about her.
I got word that she would be coming tonight...
She's here to clear her data for that
project. You know, that one they've got frozen.
The idiot watchman forgot to
give her a staff card to get around.
You can take care of this, right?
Just escort the nice young lady here to the secret base.
Oh, so that's what this is about. I see now.
Here... You need to put this on.
There are traces of quite a few erased files.
I should be able to restore them.
Impossible!
"Project Radio Noise... The goal for this
project is to resolve the genetic sequence
that gives rise to a Level 5, allowing a Level
5 that is born by chance to then be reproduced
with one hundred percent certainty...
Further...
... for this project, it has been decided...
... that Railgun... Misaka... will serve as the model."
I mean it!
There's a story going around about a
project designed to clone Level 5 espers.
Don't act like you don't remember...
It was just a little while ago.
You were walking in front of Seventh Mist...
It really exists.
A project to... to... clone me!
To create a new Railgun,
we take a fertilized egg and use a cell that has
been extracted from the original Railgun's hair follicle.
Prior to this, of course we obtained the
necessary genetic sequence pattern sample.
We were then able to successfully register
her DNA map in Academy City's databank.
In order to shorten the time
required to create a test subject...
we determined that it was necessary
to curtail the developmental process...
both physically and emotionally.
To assist with the development of the body, a
cocktail of ZID-02, RIZ-13, and HEL-03 was administered...
and in roughly fourteen days we had successfully created
a subject that was physically identical to Railgun.
The development of the mind and persona was dealt
with under the direction of external staff member
Nunotaba Shinobu, who used Testament to install
necessary basic information within the brain.
Once the results were confirmed...
everything was in order...
Project Radio Noise was set to move on to the next phase:
The mass-production of Railgun clones...
also known as Sisters.
This is what they were after?
It's the simplest thing in the world.
All you have to do is give us your DNA map, okay?
Stupid girl.
Why did you say yes to him? If only...
However...
As the project reached its final stage...
projections were calculated using Tree Diagram...
The results were not what we expected.
They used Tree Diagram?
But... that's Academy City's greatest supercomputer...
It hovers in orbit above the Earth.
Regrettably, the projections revealed
that the Sisters' specs were less than
one percent of the model Railgun's...
On average...
their ratings reached only as high as Level 2...
And even the most powerful
individuals did not exceed Level 3.
Okay, so...
They were only able to make less powerful copies...
But even if they mass-produced a lot of Level 2s...
Regardless of genetic manipulation
or acquired development...
it was impossible to produce a
Level 5 from among the clones.
Thus...
having received Tree Diagram's computed results...
and to minimize the losses incurred by this project...
the committee ordered all of the research
in progress to be terminated immediately.
The project intended to mass-produce Railgun
"Sisters" was halted and is frozen in perpetuity.
Okay... I knew it!
Of course there aren't any clones of me out there...
I'm guessing... word of this ridiculous project leaked
out some how and the Academy City rumor mill did the rest.
Whew... Even so, it's a bit freaky...
Imagine, scientists using my DNA map like that.
Well... whatever did happen, at least it's all over.
Now... I'm heading home to bed...
I wonder if Kuroko managed to trick the
Head Resident and keep me out of trouble.
Hey... how much longer is this procedure gonna take?
Total deletion will be complete... in
forty-two point two eight seconds, says Misaka,
reporting the time with careful precision.
Of course there aren't any clones of me out there!
Woah, that's a weight of my chest!
Sissy, you really can't afford to lose
any weight from your chest, you know...
I don't mean it like that!