It's your turn to answer now, Sissy.
What would you do if there was a
clone of you wandering around the city?
That's a good question...
Honestly, I would probably think it was a little
creepy and not want to hang out with her at all.
You know what I mean?
That concludes today's experiment.
I made quite a mess this time.
I wonder how long it'll take them to clean it up.
Eh... who cares?
I should stop by the store on my way home and get so...
Nice.
Awesome light show!
Picked up a new technique huh?
Controlling the iron sand using magnetism.
I have to admit, it's an interesting idea.
What? No way!
But unfortunately, once you know how
it's done, it's no big deal anymore.
I threw all that at him...
and he doesn't even have a scratch?
What the...?
Huh? That's a lot of power. Are you...
That's... impossible.
How could I not know about an esper
who can shrug off my attacks like that?
Ah, I understand now!
I was wondering what this was
since it wasn't on the schedule.
You... You're the Original.
The clones are supposed to take the Original's place.
But if I fight you...
that would considerably reduce the number of
lame combat scenarios I have to go through, right?
I'm really starting to get tired of doing this...
What do you say? Original...
Tell me why...
Why are you going along with this project?
Uh... Can we just fight?
Answer me!
You've got some serious power...
There's no way that they could force you to do anything!
So, what's your reason for participating in this insanity?
What could she have done to deserve this?
Reason? What's my reason?
That's easy...
My goal is to acquire absolute power.
Not the power of a Level 5, or Academy City's top dog.
Nothing that insignificant.
I'm talking about the kind of power that will
stop people from even thinking about challenging me.
I want invincibility.
You get that, right? Being a Level 5.
You're nuts... aren't you?
So you want to be invincible...
Is that your excuse?
Seriously? Power's not enough. You need absolute power?
That's the reason you're giving
me? The reason you agreed to kill her?
You make it sound so dirty.
Stop talking like I'm a murderer...
I'm fighting things not real people.
They're manufactured with the push of a button.
What are you so worked up about?
Oh, I get it now. I stole your thunder, huh?
That move was your ace in the
hole, and I just annihilated it.
Oh, wow...
Man, I knew you were ranked lower than me,
but I still thought you'd have more to
bring to the table than a little electricity.
All right... Now it's my turn to play...
You're in pretty rough shape,
though, so I'm not expecting too much.
But at least try to keep me entertained, okay?
Third-string?
One moment, please.
"Combat outside of the project may introduce
errors into the computational predictions. So,"
says Misaka, "this should stop now."
"Especially since Big Sister is a Level 5.
The skew from such combat would be considerable.
Rather than shortening the scheduled time... the
very project itself... would be at risk of being ruined.
Further, Misaka has, in anticipation of experiments
yet to come, received specific programming...
and any alterations to the
project would be very difficult,"
explains Misaka simply.
Tch... yeah, yeah, all right. I get
it... I was just messing around, anyway...
And stop talking like that. It's creepy.
My bad...
I guess I never introduced myself, did I?
Not satisfied with being the strongest...
You probably figured it out by now, but
I'm the one looking after your clones...
They're helping me achieve invincibility.
A Level 5 who wants to become something even greater...
There's no doubt... This boy is...
I should be grateful to you, really.
the controller of vectors...
the first-ranked esper in Academy City.
Hello there, I'm Accelerator.
It's a pleasure.
Numbers nine-nine-nine-five through
one-zero-zero-zero-seven clear the rails.
One-zero-zero-zero-eight...
What's wrong with you?
It's so screwed up...
Why are you going along with this project?
You're going to be killed... I don't get it...
Why would you do this?
Why? You're breathing, aren't you? You
have life, don't you? Isn't that enough?
Who are you?
Just who the hell are you?
What, not who... Misaka is a
product created for this project...
Artificial bodies... with artificial minds...
Laboratory animals, with a unit price
of one hundred and eighty thousand.
Goodbye then... Big Sister.
Y... Yeah... that's why I called.
She hasn't come back to the dorm yet,
so, I thought to myself, "Maybe she's at Saten's." Is she?
She hasn't stopped by here at all...
Have you tried Uiharu? Maybe she's there.
I heard from Uiharu earlier...
Uh, I mean... Yes, of course...
If she isn't at your place or here, then...
Listen, Shirai, I'm just going to throw this out there...
She could have a boyfriend.
No she couldn't! There's absolutely no way!
I'm disappointed in you, Saten! Sissy
would never do anything so improper!
She belongs to me! To me, alone, do you understand?
Hey, I was only kidding! Calm down.
Uh, hello?
Are you still there?
Geez. I wonder what that was about.
It's the simplest thing in the world. And all
you have to do is give us your DNA map, okay?
Don't do it! They're not going to use
your DNA map to cure muscular dystrophy!
They're going to use it to make clones of you!
It'll be the basis for a horrible experiment!
Say no!
No, wait! Listen to me! Please, just listen...
So that's it...
You were the cause of all this, Big Sister.
The reason Misaka was made...
The reason Misaka is killed...
All of it.
Everything.
Oh, wow... I've been here all night.
Long time no see.
I thought I spotted a delinquent
camping out all night on this bench.
I know why you're here...
You found out about the project, didn't you?
There's no way you can put a stop to it.
That's why I told you not to get involved.
No, you didn't. Oh, dear... Is that right? My mistake.
It's wrong.
How can they get away with this?
I don't know anything about Level 6 or whatever...
but is it something they want
so badly they'll kill so many?
Everyone involved with the
experiment must be completely insane.
It's not quite like that.
I won't deny that there's something crazy about it all,
but if we're talking about right
and wrong, that's another matter.
Suppose there was a way to develop a
miracle drug that could cure cancer...
but doing so would require experimental
data from twenty thousand guinea pigs.
What would you do?
You would say "we have no other choice."
That's different though.
Is it? They're both alive.
And, from a researchers perspective,
they are essentially the same thing.
The Sisters are artificially produced guinea
pigs, made for the sake of reaching Level 6...
Of course...
There are those who are in it
for their own personal gain...
and there are a few of them who
really do have a screw loose...
But across the board, none of
them recognize this as being murder.
And neither, in fact, did I.
Wasn't that the reason you were
spreading those money cards around the city?
To interfere with the experiments?
That's correct.
But why? They're not even human...
Why would you want to protect them?
Why?
As you know, Project Radio Noise was designed
in order to mass produce Level 5 espers...
When it was frozen, I left the project team...
but then... when the Sisters were
taken over by Project Level 6 Shift...
I was called in once again.
We started some in-house experiments and found there
were no particular problems with their individual minds.
The Misaka Net is in good shape.
It looks problem-free.
Want some?
I'd prefer that to having you stare at me.
What is this?
A cup of tea.
It should be included in the data input by Testament.
Misaka's first cup of tea.
"It is somewhat different than the information
in the Testament data," Misaka says curiously...
"In addition to the flavor of the tea leaves,
there is a subtle sweetness and fullness to the..."
Oh, well that would be because it's milk tea.
Basically, tea with milk added to it... It's my favorite.
Milk tea...
It's been a long time since we've met like this.
Even so... you really haven't changed much.
You're just like the first "you."
Eight thousand nine hundred and eleven units
have been consumed so far in in-house experiments...
In that time your emotional
aspects haven't developed at all...
However, your memories and experiences, in pure data form,
have all been gathered together and
shared... which is done via the Misaka Network.
And that means the next unit
will know the flavor of milk tea...
It's truly a fantastic system, the Misaka Network.
"Testament plays a very significant role,
as well, right?" Misaka asks, to clarify...
"It is through Testament that the Misakas are programmed.
That's how they learn to conceptualize
feelings and remember them as data."
"As a result of this process... the Misakas
are readily able to face the experiments,"
says Misaka, expressing gratitude.
It's time now.
You're heading out for external training...
Do you have anything to ask before you go?
What is the air outside like?
Is it sweet? Or, perhaps, spicy?
"I was told the air outside is delicious, so I'm curious.
Misaka has a preference for things that are sweet,
you see," explains Misaka shyly, revealing her tastes.
Well... you'll find out for yourself soon enough.
The glare from the sun is pretty strong today.
Pretty disappointing isn't it?
No. Not disappointing at all.
A number of aromas are stimulating my nasal
cavities... and slowly filling up my chest.
An irregular breeze blows through my hair,
sweeping past my body like a gentle touch.
Light rays from the sun beam down on my skin...
and I can feel my cheeks taking in their heat.
The outside world...
it really is a dazzling place, isn't it?
I hate to sound trite, but it was that simple.
Something changed in that moment.
From then on, I could no longer think of them as products.
Because she seemed so much more human than me...
She saw the beauty in the world... and I
could only ever see it as a warped, ugly thing.
What about you?
What do you think of them?
I'm not sure.
It's difficult to think of clones as human...
and why should I help them when they
seem so ready to accept their own deaths?
However, there are still the people who took
my DNA map and used it for their sick experiment.
Them I intend to deal with.
Yeah, that's what happened...
She called me up out of the blue, asked me
about some kind of code, and then she just...
Wait a minute. You don't know what's going on, either?
Where are you, Sissy?
Finally! Where've you been,
you could have at least called me!
Your clothes are all torn up... What happened to you?
Oh...
well, you know...
Same thing as usual...
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Um...
Hold on a second!
Hello?!
Uiharu?
Oh... yes, just n...
I mean, late last night...
That's right... There's nothing to worry about...
Please pass the message on to Haru'ue... Okay, bye.
Hello? Oh, Saten...
Yes, late last night...
I told you, you had it wrong, did I not?
Yes... it's all fine. There's
no need to worry about anything...
Right.
Listen, Kuroko. Do you have a minute?
I'm so sorry I had all of you worried.
This is my way of apologizing...
It's my treat, so go ahead, enjoy!
This is incredible.
So, spill, Misaka.
Where were you? What were you up to?
I wanted to do... some stargazing.
Stargazing?
Yep... that's right.
Well, you know...
Like every now and again, when you
get into a schmaltzy kind of mood.
And you just want to sit on the swings
in the park, swaying back and forth,
humming cheesy songs to yourself
and staring at the stars...
You get it.
No, I don't...
I don't even know what "schmaltzy" means.
Oh you don't, huh?
Well, it's just how I was feeling last night.
I meant to ask: Did you ever figure
out what that code was for yesterday?
What do you mean?
Oh, it was just...
A... Ah, the code!
Well that was... it was...
What is it, Sissy?
Are you okay?
Please, Misaka, is something wrong?
I can see you.
All of you...
I can see you there beside me... but I can't... I can't...
What are you saying?
The arcade!
Let's go to the arcade, Misaka!
It's been a long time... and I want
to take on the punching machine again.
Great idea! The arcade!
Oh... in that case, I want to do one of these again.
Oh, yeah, I remember.
We'll do that, too!
Let's go, let's go!
We need to clear our heads.
You guys...
Just one thing... I want you to remember this, Misaka.
No matter what, we're always here for you.
If your burden is ever too heavy, just say the word, okay?
Mmm.
It really has been a long time, hasn't it?
A long, long time!
I wonder if the moles are still there.
I'll show you the technique I have for that game.
Yes. I can see now.
I'm takin' you down, just wait!
All the more reason...
However, there are still the people who took my
DNA map and used it for their sick experiment...
Them I intend to deal with.
Well, aren't you a defiant one?
It isn't just one facility...
There are more than twenty.
Are you planning to do this alone?
Yes, I am... No one else needs to get involved.
I'm the one who made this mess.
I will be the one...
...to clean it up.
Ugh... I'm still worried about Misaka.
So am I.
Time for a snack!
Shirai?
It's Anshindo's special, magical,
limited-time-only summer buns!