Come on!
What is with this thing?
Is that...
We got ourselves a cutie here...
Oooh... and she's from Tokiwadai, too.
Wanna come with us; have some fun tonight?
We'll even take you back to your dorm...
Of course, there's no telling
how late it might be by then.
What do these idiots think they're
going to accomplish by talking to me?
Pathetic.
Everyone else is pretending not to see.
It's not that they don't care.
They just can't do anything about it.
If they interfered, they'd only get themselves hurt.
And that wouldn't help anyone.
Everyone has to look out for themselves...
That's the way it works.
And if there is somebody out there who would
jump in the middle of this to help out a stranger...
Well, that person is just a fool.
Oh, hey, there you are!
Thanks for keeping her company, guys!
You shouldn't wander off like
that. You know how much I worry!
I gave it plenty of money.
I don't understand...!
Is it out of order?
Seriously?!
Heh.
Please don't screw with me today...
Give me back my money!
Are you done yet?
You just going to stand there like an idiot?
Are you gonna buy something or not?
What? Hold on...
I seriously need to rehydrate.
If I don't get a drink, I could
pass out at any given moment.
You're one rude chick.
When will you get it through your thick skull?
My name is Mikoto Misaka!
Is it really that hard for you to remember?!
Great.
So I guess that hasn't changed either, huh...?
Why is it that my shocks have no effect on you?
I don't know!
But it serves you right for using your ability like that!
Well...
if you're done, I'm going to get what I came for.
I've got some serious business with this vending machine.
Uh... about this machine...
It has a tendency to eat your money.
Not five minutes ago, it took mine and gave me nothing.
So, you got yoinked?
Well, what was the damage...?
How much did it take you for?
2000.
Wow! 2000?! You gave it that big of a bill?
Then of course it ate your money, you idiot!
I can't tell you how much I needed a laugh...
So... I'll get you your money's worth.
Eh?
Yeah...
This machine and I go way back.
You wouldn't believe how much money I...
Hmm?
Uh, never mind...
Anyway, like I said, I'm going to make
this thing give you what you paid for.
Uh, you know...
I don't have a good feeling about this.
Just forget it.
Hah!
Thank you for waiting.
No problem.
So, that's it?
She's back to normal, just like that?
Uh-huh.
And just when I had decided to leave her
alone and wait for her to confide in me.
There's no reason for Sissy to know how worried I've been.
All that would do is make her worry, instead.
I just hope we never have to go through that again.
Hmm...
Let's recap.
She went out last night without eating anything...
She didn't give us any details about
where she was going or what she was doing...
It fits.
I'm sure now. There can only be one explanation...
There's a boy involved...
There must be. I wonder who it is.
Oh! W... W... Wow!
Absolutely not! There's no boy!
That's why she's been acting so strangely because...
That's right. Because she's lovestruck.
It all makes sense now!
Why she was sneaking around.
Why she couldn't turn to any of us for advice.
Why she kept it all completely secret...
I know!
I wonder what type of boy Misaka would choose.
I'll bet he's a gallant young gentleman
and as handsome as a prince, too!
Well, handsome is always a plus...
but I think Misaka would also want to go out
with a guy who was intelligent and interesting.
Wait! She stays out all night and
doesn't come home until morning...
You don't think she could be...
Are you okay, Uiharu?
No... there's no way...
Of all people, Sissy wouldn't...
An alarm?
What the... you guys are really quick.
Just listen...
That sounds like an alarm from a vending machine, right?
Well, what do you think?
A vending machine in that direction?
Could it be...?
So, what should we do, Shirai?
I'm gonna go see what might've set it off.
Well then, I'll come, too.
That's okay If I need backup, I'll contact you.
Hold on!
Wait up!
What are you so scared of?
I can't... run any farther...
Honestly!
You could at least help me carry all this stuff!
I did my part. I made that machine
cough up everything it owed you.
Well, I didn't want to steal any...
Technically, they already belong to you.
If I accept this, I'm not a bystander, but an accomplice.
Here.
There's more where that came from.
Whoa!
Hold on! Hold on! Ow!
There are some hot ones in there, too!
It's not my fault.
I can't choose what kind of drink it spits out, you know.
What's with you, anyway?
The littlest thing is enough to send you running...
It doesn't help my pride that the
guy who beat me is a big crybaby!
Huh? What did you say?
Please! Don't act like you don't remember. You managed
to defeat me, both in town and out by the riverbed.
Wait, so I've been getting into
fights with a middle-school girl?
Really? You're actually trying
to pretend that you've forgotten?
How pathetic can you be?
What have I been doing?
Whatever, just drink...
You should be thankful. I can think of at least
one girl who would swoon to get a present from me.
Aw, gimme a break.
This isn't some manga...
Girls don't actually "swoon."
Heh... if only that were true.
Of course, you probably don't know what
they call me at Tokiwadai Middle School, do you?
Hi, Sissyyyyy!
I heard a vending machine alarm, so I came running.
And sure enough, here you are!
Here we go. Speak of the devil...
What's up?
Uh, something wrong, Kuro...
Geez! What's the matter with you?
I thought she was wrong... but it's true!
How awful!
You're having a secret assignation with a boy!
Hold on a minute!
It's a pleasure to meet you, gentleman caller.
Whoa, what now?
The name's Kuroko Shirai, and I have
the honor of being Mikoto's right hand gal.
Her one and only partner. Forever.
As you appear to be an acquaintance of Sissy's,
I am bound by social etiquette to
at least introduce myself to you.
Uh... okay...
Are you kidding me?
He's not exactly what you would call "impressive."
Could someone like him really be with Sissy?
My, it doesn't take very much
to incapacitate him, does it?
I thought you would have had better taste than this.
Excuse me?
Do you seriously think a blithering idiot
like this is my boyfriend? How stupid can you be?!
Wait! Your what?!
No, of course I didn't...!
I thought it seemed like a strange pairing.
Come on!
Get back down here!
Let me think.
Of course, I would love for you to
wash your hands of this troglodyte
and allow me to escort you back home to our room, but...
it might be best for you to build up some immunity to the
charms of men so you are not led further astray later on.
And, really...
I don't think I have anything to fear
from this helpless, goofy little monkey...
In fact, it's possible that he's so pathetic that
you will become disillusioned with men in general,
and then I will be there to console you!
And, besides...
You finally seem like yourself again.
I said, are you listening?!
I have nothing more to say... and, as I have
some things to attend to, I will take my leave.
I'm sure I can trust you not to
embarrass yourself here, Sissy...
Hey!
So Good-bye.
What do you mean by that?!
She vanished!
Saying something like that, and then running away!
So there are people in real
life who use the term "Sissy"...
I had no idea...
You Tokiwadai girls are something else.
She's actually sort of a special case.
Oh... Is she?
Oh, man! Why am I here?
I need some rest.
Big Sister?
She's back... Wait... what the...
You mean... There's another Zapper?
"Our appearances are, indeed, similar.
Which makes sense, as we are entirely identical
on a genetic level." Offers Misaka in reply.
Huh? A genetic level...?
Oh, ah! So you guys're twins, huh?
Moments ago... I identified a power
identical to Misaka's being used in the area.
When I arrived, I found a broken vending machine.
And now I see you with all of these beverages.
Big Sister, I hope I am wrong in suspecting
that you are an accomplice to theft.
Hey!
Your sister is the perpetrator!
I'm an innocent bystander!
Misaka investigated...
I checked for fingerprints using my ability.
The results showed that the
most recent set belonged to you.
No way! You can actually tell?
Kidding.
Not laughing...!
Give me a break!
This sister of yours could stand to learn...
Uh...
Why?
Of all places...
What are you doing wandering around out here?
I am here for training.
But...
What are you training for?
Are you joining Judgment or something?
Judgment?
Oh, yeah... that's what this is.
Come on. Let's talk.
Unfortunately, Misaka has a schedule to keep.
It's okay!
Come with me.
Well, every family is different...
Some more than others...
Big Sister... how far are we going to walk?
Misaka's schedule is already off by
thirty-eight seconds. She must go soon.
The experiment...
The project was shut down, wasn't it?
So why?
"To which project are you referring?
Could you be inquiring about Project Level 6 Shift...?
If so, it is proceeding on schedule."
Misaka says to clarify.
But it's not...!
Still?
Mm. Yes... That is correct...
Experiment Number 10020 was just conducted.
That's ten...
thousand?
What is she saying?
No... They can't...
I thought they went bankrupt!
I read it, but I don't understand...
How could they...
It isn't over yet!
They're still... killing those girls!
No... that's not true.
It was me... I killed them.
And her, too...
Soon, she'll be...
Big Sister?
Are you all...
Aww! How adorable!
"Misaka found the cute animal,"
says Misaka, trumpeting her achievement.
What do I do now...?
What more...
can I possibly do?
Big Sister...
Big Sister, it's a kitty-kiddy.
Big Sister... Big Sister... Big Sister...
No, stop it!
Please, stop it!
I can't take it...
You showing up like this...
Looking like you do! Just go away, all right?!
Okay.
Misaka will leave now.
It keeps getting worse.
Man.
These are heavy!
I wonder what was up with Zapper and her sister...
That was strange.
Whoa!
Aww man, that's gonna leave a bruise.
"You've fallen.
Do you need a hand getting up?"
Misaka asks, offering her help, somewhat reluctantly.
Thanks a lot, Zapper.
Oh, you aren't her. You're the sister.
Wait... I thought you guys wandered
off for a heart-to-heart or something.
"Misaka was there before, and now she is here,"
says Misaka, pointing.
"After we gather them,
where would you like to take these canned beverages?"...
Asks Misaka, cleaning up your mess.
Oh, uh, don't worry about it!
Really, I can carry them myself...
"After we have picked them up,
where should we take these beverages?"
Misaka asks, repeating the question.
Hello.
Is something the matter?
You look awfully flushed, Dr. Amai...
Are you all right?
Don't "Hello" me!
How could you involve so many facilities?!
We're supposed to be taking the lead on Level 6 Shift!
If you scatter the work around
like this, the patent will never be...
Now, now, let's calm down.
We could divide it up even more than this,
and there would still be plenty of profit.
You can't possibly know that!
Oh, but I can.
Listen...
Right now, what's most important
is completing the experiments.
A total of a hundred and eighty-three
facilities are receiving transfers.
Quite a lot.
If that breaks our mysterious
attacker's spirit, then good...
And should the attacks continue, well...
The more of those facilities that are destroyed...
the greater our share of the profit becomes, doesn't it?
There're so many...
one-hundred-eighty-three...
How could it have been spread between
that many facilities in such a short time?
How could one firm possibly operate on this high a level?
Oh, wow...
I'm an idiot...
I can't believe I didn't see it sooner.
Academy City is under satellite and
camera surveillance twenty-four hours a day...
There's no way that the city's senior management
could have failed to notice these twisted experiments
when they were being held over and over again outside.
In other words...
All of Academy City...
is my enemy.
Ugh...
No flavor left in that piece.
Hello. Have a sec?
So, which lab's errand boy are you?
What makes you think I'm with a lab?
Only two types of people ever come near me...
There are the ones who want to
use me for scientific analysis.
And then there are the idiots who want to fight me
so they can claim the title of Academy City's top dog.
Hmm... that's very interesting.
Though, as both types tend to be full of crap,
I don't see all that much difference between them.
It's called Level 6 Shift?
Yeah...
An experiment with Tree Diagram's endorsement.
Ha! I'll pass, thanks.
I'm the first-ranked esper in Academy City...
and that means I'm already at the top of the heap, buddy.
No one can beat me...
No matter who they are or what
they try, I'll win every single time.
So why should I care about
becoming any stronger than I am now?
You're right about one thing...
You are definitely the strongest esper in the city.
However...
grand as it is, is that title gonna be enough for you?
Doesn't it make life a bit monotonous?
Just imagine...
If you were to gain even greater power...
absolute power...
Then what would your life be like?
More interesting, I would think.
Even more power than I already have...
Really?
I'm glad you decided to come.
Mass-production of clones, in
violation of international law.
I gotta admit, I'm impressed.
You guys are a special kind of crazy.
Actually, they were originally intended
for use in a completely different project...
but things happen...
So all of them wound up being handed over to us.
Now that you've seen them...
Are you still interested in achieving Level 6?
Only another nine thousand nine
hundred and seventy left to go, huh?
What a drag.
Okay, Sissy!
The bathtub is all yours if you want it!
Alright, thank you.
What happened?
She was in such good spirits this afternoon.
Don't tell me it was that troglodyte!
He shall pay for this!
What can I do?
Do I have any moves left?
Find the mastermind and put the screws to him...?
No. If Academy City is green-lighting
these experiments, that won't do any good...
Who would come up with such a
messed-up project in the first place?
I get it.
That's why they aren't printing anything about my attacks!
They don't want to risk the public finding
out about their illegal cloning experiments.
But... maybe... if I were to destroy it...
Academy City would have nowhere to turn.
If I did that...
My life could never be normal again.
What am I thinking?
They've already killed ten thousand of me,
and I'm worried about living a normal life?
Hey... Kuroko...
Sissy...? Can I help you with something?
Supposing... just supposing...
I did something that brought
calamity and chaos to Academy City...
What would you do?
Hmm...
If you mean making off with drinks
from a vending machine that you damaged,
I guess I would suggest not doing it again...
That thing is fair game as far as I'm concerned!
It stole money from me my first year here!
No, I mean...
If I did something...
something that affected the very core of Academy City...
I cannot pretend to know why you
would even ask a question like that.
But if someone did something to threaten the safety
of this city, I wouldn't hesitate to take action...
Even if that somebody was you, Sissy.
Then, despite all the things you've said,
I suppose our relationship really does have its limits.
No, it doesn't at all!
Because in a million years, I know there isn't even
a remote chance that you would ever do anything to...
Hah! Gotcha!
I'm just messing with ya.
That wasn't nice, Sissy!
Thank goodness.
Ooh... come a little bit closer, Sissy...
If I put a stop to the project
and Kuroko's the one to catch me...
Well...
That wouldn't be so bad.
I knew it was a boy!
Absolutely not! One hundred percent not a boy!
A boy! No it isn't!...