The idealist will say...
No man has inherent superiority.
That we are, all of us, beings of equal worth.
While the spiritualist will argue...
No effort goes unrewarded.
So, endeavor we must...
For, it is the process itself that is important.
Of course... all of that's a lie.
Every child learns one thing
quickly, living in this city...
It doesn't matter how much you study...
or how great of a thesis you produce...
In this city, you're either an esper or you're neglected.
A person's ability determines their worth...
their standing...
It is the one and only benchmark.
However, abilities are such unpredictable things...
They're affected by one's innate qualities,
and only in the rarest instance
is a high-level esper produced,
yet they are an important part of our social structure.
So, you see...
I could not help thinking to myself...
What if I could create my own esper?
I could use an approach that differs
completely from the existing methods.
I could design an esper that
was both stable and consistent...
but because it was artificially produced
would not be too valuable to be quickly used up.
So I collaborated with a few like-minded individuals,
and together we bent our minds
to developing a certain project.
One that would allow us to create
an esper with absolute certainty.
"Project Chemicaloid" was born.
And that project...
It produced Febri and her sister...
They exist because of your petty ambitions.
Heh... Yes, you would say that...
Like most people in this city, you
are entrenched in ability Levelism.
I've dealt with your kind.
What do you mean?
You see... I have presented this project
to people with skills like yours before,
skills that would be necessary for a chemicaloid.
How is it someone from the
underground is so short-sighted?
You would think they would see
the potential in our proposal.
I'm glad you made it here safely.
Now we can finally implement Project Level 6 Shift
on the scale that we had originally planned for it.
Ah! Is that... Dr. Gensei Kihara?
I have to admit I began to sweat
when I heard there was some competition.
Oh, was there?
Ah! You mean the one where they
wanted to grow espers like sea-monkeys?
From that I learned a valuable lesson...
Even famous intellectual minds
can be clouded by an outdated
obsession with esper Levelism.
Revolutionary ideas are always
initially suspect, after all.
To be recognized we would have to
prove ourselves on intellect alone...
and so we produced what we said we would all along.
Chemicaloids.
Products that would prove our
worth... our true superiority...
to this city...
indeed, to the whole world!
So... what is it about these chemicaloids
that proves how superior you are?
What ability do your "products" have?
Trying to draw information out of me?
Now, now, I've already given you a good number of clues.
Remote operation...
With a strand of hair acting as a medium.
Well... that's part of it, but certainly not all...
Nice effort, though, Railgun.
Want to know more?
Well... You will...
After much waiting, at day break tomorrow, we
will begin our large-scale chemicaloid experiment.
Experiment?
No...
that word really isn't big enough anymore...
Allow me to revise.
Revolution!
STUDY Corporation will turn Academy City on it's head!
We will teach this wretched city...
No! We will teach the whole world a lesson!
Ultimately, progress is not brought about by abilities...
but by intelligence!
I...
feel...
Is that the time...
really?
Don't bother trying to move.
Only your eyes and your mouth will respond.
Your body is paralyzed.
It's because of the drug...
the one I injected you with...
It blocks the transmission of
commands to your nervous system.
You won't be able to move a finger for two more hours yet.
So... I'm curious...
How did you... get involved with these people?
I remember what you said.
You talked to me before about my sisters...
about how you stopped seeing them as things
and were trying to shut down the experiments...
After all that...
why get mixed up in something like this?
During the Sisters case, I made a mistake.
I was caught by an underground organization.
And then... I was sold.
To STUDY.
That's when I was introduced to
the artificially created twins.
Their names were Janie and Febri.
The involuntary neural activity
essential to keeping them alive...
what you might call their core programming...
was based on a thesis that I had written a long time ago.
That particular sin
is one for which I will never be forgiven...
It will follow me my entire life.
Even so...
I must keep trying...
I must atone by helping in whatever way is possible...
That was all I could think... when I saw those girls.
Janie...
That's Febri's sister...
She only has enough programming language installed
to allow her Diffusion Ghost core to function properly.
Diffusion Ghost?
That is Janie's ability...
I'd planned to give her consciousness
comparable to that of a normal girl...
I'd get my hands on the neutralizing agent...
and then I would run away with her.
But now...
Things have gone too far... and that isn't possible.
I have to get the formula from Aritomi.
That's the only choice, since
he's the one who came up with it...
I'll do whatever I have to go get it from him.
Yes. I see.
I don't care what happens to me...
I will save those girls...
no matter the cost.
I get it...
I understand her guilt.
Hey...
I know what I've done is unforgivable...
My sister never got the chance, but...
she wanted to tell you thanks.
You think you have to do this by yourself...
but if you take a look around,
I think you'll realize you're wrong...
You're not alone...
There are people out there who
want to help you if you'll let them.
And you're one of those people I suppose?
But how do you think you can help me right now...?
You're effectively paralyzed...
Thanks to me, the only thing you can move is your mouth!
Oh, really? Just my mouth... huh?
How can you...?
Incredible!
She's using her ability to directly control
the electrical signals that run to her nerves!
I've never tried this before.
But, hey... it seems to work pretty well, huh?
Doing something like that should be causing
intense pain throughout her entire body.
Let me tell you what I've come to realize recently...
Other people count on you...
but you can count on them, too...
If you work with someone instead of on your own,
your combined strength can make all the difference.
You know...
when I first found out about my sisters...
I reacted the same way you are...
I just kept thinking...
"This is my fault. I have to do something."
However...
It took a while, but I've finally stopped
thinking like that... Which is why...
Here they come.
Huh?
Hey! What's going on?
More intruders...
The guard robots are down.
Uiharu...
I've got the entrance under my control.
You're certain there are no civilians in the area?
Yes, the coast is clear...
You can do whatever you need to...
Come in, Saten. What's the status outside?
It's all good...
No suspicious activity so far.
How did they know where to find you?
I borrowed one of those implantable tracking devices
they use when you go outside of Academy City.
And then...
I talked it over with my friends.
I told them if I was gone too long,
they should come and get me.
You actually dragged your friends into this mess...
No.
I explained the situation to them...
and then I asked. I asked for help.
And without hesitation, they agreed...
They care about Febri, too.
Although... it looks like Febri may need more help
than my friends and I can give.
So now I'm asking you...
Do you think you can help us save her?
But this is all my fault. You can't trust me.
Yes I can.
I trust you completely.
Look...
No, this is all wrong...
you shouldn't be saying that.
I'm the one who should be asking you...
So, now I am...
I'm asking... Please help us!
Kuroko!
Hi, Sissy!
Ah... Hold on. You don't want to...
Ahh!
How cruel!
I came to help and you repay me like this?!
I'm... sorry... It's kind of a long story,
but basically I'm going to be a human stun gun
for a little while.
Huh?
Anyway... I think we've worn out our welcome.
What's going on?
I'll explain soon enough.
Let's get out of here.
She regained all motor function
after a full dose of the drug...
Incredible.
It seems she's every bit as strong as we'd heard.
So... what are you still doing here...?
Why didn't you run away?
What choice did I have?
Everybody knows my history...
that I was sold to your corporation.
If I ran, then the entire underworld would be after me.
In this town, that's as good as a death sentence.
So, you stayed out of fear rather than loyalty...
That's not surprising...
It's just as well, however. If you weren't here to assist,
we'd have to resort to the whip when using Janie.
The only place you have left is
here in the darkness with STUDY.
For your own good, I do hope you'll keep that in mind.
Are you sure you want to stay?
Aritomi is cautious...
He doesn't want to be discovered...
He's relocated Janie some place else.
If I leave, we won't be able to find out where she is now.
But you...
Don't worry about me.
I still have at least a little value to them...
They won't dispose of me right away...
I just have to bide my time...
I'll find out where their base is
and I'll get the formula we need.
Just be careful.
Anyway... about what Aritomi said...
He mentioned something was going to happen tomorrow.
What's that all about, do you know?
They haven't given me any of the details...
But like he said, they do have something planned.
Tomorrow.
A terrorist attack at the Reach Assembly sites?
Yes...
Actually, the word he used to
describe it was "revolution."
That sounds crazy!
These guys mean business...
They have Febri's sister,
Janie, and they plan on using her.
Or, at any rate... they'll use Janie's ability.
Huh?!
No way!
Sorry, but did you say "Diffusion
Ghost" was the name of her ability?
Her ability is called "Diffusion Ghost,"
and it requires hair for a medium...
With it, she is able to convert the AIM diffusion fields
in an enclosed space into virtual matter
and achieve control.
In other words, those empty powered suits
and the berserk security robots were controlled
in the same way... With Janie... And her strange ability.
This use of AIM fields sounds familiar to me.
Like what Dr. Kiyama did that one time.
You understand this?
Kind of...
I do think I've seen it...
Let's think...
With operating system abilities,
there is a limit to how many
things can be controlled at once...
This isn't really suited for a large-scale attack.
Okay, but...
they did say that a number of simple commands
are placed ahead of time into the fields
that Janie virtually materializes...
For example...
"Eliminate any opponent who attacks."
Something like that.
So, basically...
it's like having a bunch of
autonomous robots on hand, right?
If all this is true...
a large-scale attack wouldn't be impossible.
Febri's sister.
Do you know where STUDY has been keeping Janie...?
If we stop her, they can't launch an attack!
Well, yeah, that's true...
but this Nunotaba woman I mentioned to you before...
she wasn't told what the base
for the attack was going to be.
Oh, no...
Once Janie uses her ability,
Nunotaba thinks Febri will be able to
give us an idea of her sister's location,
or at least the direction of where to start looking.
That's all well and good, but...
If she's used her ability, doesn't
that mean that we are already too late?
If we're going to forestall this,
the best thing to do would be
to pursue the powered suit angle.
There must be quite a number of them currently deployed
in the area around the Reach Assembly site...
Uiharu... look that up?
I have more parameters to apply to the search now...
I think I can do it!
Hey, you know...
with all this new information,
Antiskill might be able to act.
You're right!
I'm sorry, I really am.
But I don't think Antiskill can get involved in this case.
But why not?
The STUDY Corporation, huh?
Now that I hear that name,
things are starting to make sense.
They're fairly new...
but they've quickly risen to prominence, forcing out
the competition to become our equipment suppliers...
Their swift ascent has been bothering me...
but, I guess this explains it.
Mm. Ya' know, for that matter,
it explains why I was suddenly suspended, too.
Suspended?!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm weathering the storm at a friend's place...
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
I'm a lot more worried about you guys.
Don't do anything crazy.
The situation is even more dire than we first thought.
I've got it!
The record of STUDY Corporation's bulk
containers and the sites they have been delivered to.
They made it into the sites? How could they...
Well, look.
It says here that there was a
blackout at each site during delivery,
and all of their records appear to be incomplete.
Blackouts! Of course!
And now we know the reason behind them.
How many are we talking about?
Give me a second. I'm tallying them now.
Bad news, ladies!
I finally got a hold of some relevant information
using my father's channels...
When you add up...
Approximating by container capacity and contents...
you've got enough to build a truly incredible
number of powered suits!
No way! That's so many!
The number has to be...
Over 20,000!
I beg your pardon?
Impossible...
The thing is...
Since they went through official
channels to deliver the suits
to all of the various sites...
we can't take any action without Antiskill's cooperation.
If we do, there's a good chance we'd be arrested.
Essentially... it doesn't sound like there's a
whole lot we can do until they make their move.
Then we have to find this Janie girl and stop her somehow.
Yes, except... we have no way of knowing
where she is until she activates her ability.
Which means we'll have to allow the attack to begin.
That's crazy!
We're totally unprepared...
These guys are light years ahead of us.
All this time...
they've been getting ready for a coup.
If they get out into the city,
who knows how much damage they'll do?
What's on your mind?
Please tell us.
I just want to save Febri...
and her sister, Janie as well...
I want to save Nunotaba,
who, right now, is still embedded with the enemy...
And, of course, I want to protect Academy City.
I also...
I want to keep every single one of you out of danger...
So, I wonder... am I just being selfish?
Well, if you are...
If that's the case, then I have to admit I'm selfish, too.
Mm-Hm. And actually... I may be worse...
because I want all of that, and on top of it,
I want you to stop looking so miserable.
Saten is right.
Even when things are going as well as they can...
you still seem to find something to worry about, Sissy...
It makes it hard for the rest
of us to really relax, you know?
That's true...
Cheer up. We can do this if we all work together.
Exactly...!
Together, there's nothing we can't do!
I... I believe so, as well...
We are unstoppable.
It won't be easy...
but when this is finally over...
we'll still be standing, shoulder to shoulder.
We'll have a happy ending, you'll see!
I know you have your own goals...
Mine is seeing everybody get through this alive.
Heh. I know what you mean.
Now it's my goal too.
Uh?
Oh, hi... Everybody's here.
Yes, Febri...
we are all here...
and we're about to go and see if we can help Janie.
Would you like to come, too?
Yeah!
Heh.
Oh, Aomi?
Sorry to be calling you so late.
That's okay.
If you're the one calling,
well, I know there's a good reason,
no matter how late it might be.
So, spill.
All right. Tell me...
What do you think about this city?
Huh?
Thank you, Father, I really appreciate this.
Okay... I'll leave you to it, then.
Heh. Well, you heard her.
Let's indulge my daughter.
You'll see to everything... right, Pops?
Oh, hot! Hot! Hot!
All done!
Wow! That's very pretty!
I'm gonna save it so my sister can eat it.
That's so sweet...
And how is it going over there?
Hmm. I'm not sure how well it's going,
but I'm not giving up anytime soon, I promise that much!
Hang in there!
You bet!
Okay! We'll keep working hard, too, right, Febri?
That's refreshing! Ahh...
I've got everything all ready to go over here, too.
This should make a good decoy
in case the head resident comes barging in here.
Wait.
This only makes it look like
one of us is sleeping, doesn't it?
And this side is too big...
See... they are sleeping... in each other's arms!
Oww!
Aww. But I had them positioned just right.
Good grief.
We can at least try to make it look realistic.
If we get found out, we're both in for it.
Let's see...
Hey, Sissy...
What's this?
It's a four-leaf clover.
Huh?
It's a good-luck charm that I picked especially for you.
Thanks a lot.
By the way...
Who was that you called earlier?
Oh... Just someone.
Ten minutes remaining to sunrise.
It has been a long night, indeed.
But, at last...
we are about to see the dawning of a new day.
All systems are prepped and ready to go.
All that remains is to activate them.
Janie has reached critical phase, as well...
It's almost as if she's aware
of her own role in what's to come.
Almost time...
What I have planned may work, and it may not...
Either way, it won't absolve my sin.
But... even so...
I resolve to do whatever I can.
Now then. Time for final confirmation...
Those in favor or proceeding as we have planned?
Okay, we're ready...
Let us begin our Silent Party.
You know, you look very nice in that outfit.
Is that the present Kongo bought for you?
Mm-Hmm. It's pretty,
and it reminds me of the one from before.
One from before?
From Shinobu... She picked it out for me.
Oh?
Well...
It's time now.
All right!
You will not be taking...
one tiny little step...
beyond this point.
You... you go right ahead...
and give us the best you've got to give!
That way!
My sister...
Here. Don't forget this.
This is our last shot.
Up you go...
I need you to trust me, okay?
Aaaahhhhh!
Right... Here we go!
To protect Academy City...
To save Janie and Febri...
and Nunotaba, too.
For a happy ending for all of us!
That's why we're fighting...
To make that dream come true!