So, all told.
What was our assignment this time, anyway?
Yeah.
That's an ultra-good question.
Well, we were supposed to come down
here and put a stop to an arms deal.
Of course, we get here, and there's no arms deal in sight
and instead, one of these toys starts attacking us.
You look funny. What's the deal?
I dunno. I have this feeling.
Mugino!
Thank you for that.
Ultra happy to be of service.
Geez, don't startle me like that, okay?
Thank you, Mugin...
Tch.
I'd say those are adequate
enough results for a field test.
We are steadily gathering data for the real thing.
Aritomi.
Huh?
Oh, man. I've got a tummy ache!
That was an exotic stew. I've never eaten turtle before.
The beef Misaka brought was amazing, too.
And because of that, I am now way too full!
Maybe we should find some medicine for you.
Oh, by the way.
Did that talk you had with your teacher go all right?
Yeah. It did. I think we found the perfect spot.
You did, huh?
Then it's almost time.
Mm.
So?
Who's that you were talking to?
Hm?
That fine young man back there.
Oh, just somebody I know.
So evasive!
Ooh! It was cookie boy, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't!
I swear, that's the last time I bake anything!
Okay, fine,
if that wasn't him, who is the cookie guy?
I... I'm telling you he...
Hello, Sissy.
You're getting here late. What have you been up to?
Ooh, I'll tell you.
Ah! Hey, look, the elevator's here!
Come on, come on, let's go! Quickly now, everybody! Heh.
There she goes! So adorable!
Congratulations, Edasaki.
Huh?
We hear you're being discharged. Right?
Heh, yeah I am! I owe it all to you guys.
Having that uniform waiting
for me really inspired me to work
hard and finish my rehabilitation before summer was over!
So, is everything set for when you get out of here?
Mm-Hmm.
Actually, Edasaki is going to be living with Haru'ue.
Oh. Really?
Yep.
Well, you know. I've been in a home for so long.
Suddenly living on her own would be really hard.
I talked to my teachers about the situation,
and they agreed that Banri and I could share a place.
Oh, that's nice.
So then, you'll be moving again, huh?
We'd be happy to come by and help you guys out.
That's okay, thanks though.
Uiharu and I already took care of it.
Seriously?
Yep.
We made a few calls and got
the movers lined up for tomorrow.
Well, that was quick.
You could have at least asked us.
Haru'ue said there's still some stuff
she and Edasaki needed to talk about.
Oh, okay.
Really, Uiharu, if you'd just said something,
we totally would have helped out on moving day.
Don't worry about it.
It's honestly not that big a deal.
Though the whole place is overflowing
with cardboard boxes right now.
Yeah, I can imagine.
I remember what it was like when
Haru'ue first moved in with you.
There's even more now than there was then.
Which is strange since she didn't
actually live there for that long.
Oh, I forgot!
Huh?
We have to go.
It's about time, isn't it, Shirai?
Oh. Yeah, you're right. It is.
What? You guys have some kinda' Judgment work to do?
Yeah. We've been asked to do security
for the upcoming Academic Reach Assembly.
Today's the preliminary inspection.
Oh.
Sorry.
Hm?
I don't really understand what a
school assembly would need security for.
Uh?
Oh! I can see why you were confused.
Shirai wasn't using its full name,
the Academy City Research Forum Assembly.
It's called "Academic Reach" for short.
Academy City's students are
dedicated to research and study.
Those with outstanding grades are given a setting
in which they can share their work with others.
That's what the Academy City Research Forum Assembly is.
Qualification for the forum is based on
the strength of students' academic work,
rather than the strength of their abilities.
Oh, I see.
Well, that sounds kinda fun.
It's like a festival for smart people.
Maybe not quite as fun as a festival.
There are professional quality presentations,
great lectures, and all sorts of other stuff.
Yeah?
I don't really get it, but I guess it sounds cool.
I wonder why they picked this
year to start doing this thing.
Eh...
Uh, Saten.
They actually do it every year.
Seriously?
Wow!
You mean you're really going to help us?
It's a request from a member of the swim club.
But since you're not in the
club, you certainly don't have to...
Oh, nonsense. Don't be silly.
Club member or not, you two are my
friends, so I would be happy to assist you.
Besides, I'm still relatively new to the area, you know.
So I've never seen an Academic Reach Assembly before.
This would be a perfect opportu...
Kongo! Are you all right?
You ruffian!
You dare to assault Mitsuko Kongo?
Somebody, please help!
That man took my bag!
It is the height of stupidity
to perpetrate such a brazen theft
in broad daylight on a busy street!
You're a moron and a criminal.
And I will not allow you to roam the streets any longer.
You're done.
Mitsuko Kongo has spoken!
Kongo always comes through.
She is so amazing!
Now to dispose of him.
Wannai, there is an Antiskill
station just around the corner.
Would you please alert them?
Yes, right away!
A good day's work.
Excuse me.
Do you have a moment?
I saw this little scene play out.
Don't you think you went a bit too far?
What?
It doesn't matter whether this man
is a purse-snatching miscreant or not.
I don't think you should be
using your ability so recklessly.
Oh? And who are you to say...
There were a number of ways
that you could have handled this.
And any one of them would have been better.
Like you told those other girls.
There's an Antiskill booth not far away from here,
and don't forget the security cameras.
What exactly are you...
If I may continue.
Did you not even stop for a moment to think
how much danger you were exposing everybody here to?
Huh?
You didn't notice this, did you?
Fortunately for us, you were able to
incapacitate him with one shot this time.
Can you begin to imagine the
results if you had failed to do so?
The thief would have been furious.
He may even have taken a woman or child hostage.
Ya' know, he's right about that!
That would've been awful.
Those abilities aren't foolproof.
You seem to be quite confident of yourself and your power.
But an ability isn't always the answer.
I didn't mean to.
Hold on a minute!
I don't know who you are or why you're here.
But there's no reason to be so hard on her.
Whether you approve or not, the fact
remains that she did safely secure the criminal.
Ladies, you're back.
I'm really sorry we took so long.
The Antiskill officers are on their way down here now.
Oh. That's good, thank you.
He's gone.
I wonder where he could've run off to.
What a strange man.
Hey Sissy, I'm home.
Hey.
You were gone for a while.
Ugh...
What's up? You seem exhausted.
The preliminary Reach inspection.
I knew the forum was being held across
several different universities, but still.
I didn't expect to have to walk that much.
I think my feet might fall off.
Judgment's a pretty tough gig, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Uiharu was with you, right?
How is she doing?
The same as she always is.
She carried out her duties admirably.
That's good.
With the move and everything.
Moving can be hard, you know.
I mean, remember how big of a mess
it was when you first moved in here?
Are you really bringing up that whole thing again?
The statute of limitations.
What's up, Sissy?
Thinking about old times.
Pretty crazy, huh?
Ah! Well... yeah.
Hmm... I know!
Since you're so exhausted, I could give you a massage.
I could give you a massage.
I could give you a massage. I could give you a massage.
Kuroko?
Whoa! What the...
Well, I just.
I thought I would take a shower first.
Right.
Ui-ha-ru!
C'mon, Saten, is that absolutely necessary?
'Kay, I'm sorry.
Were you waiting for me or something?
What? Oh, no.
I was just in the area, so.
I really am fine. I promise.
Haru'ue and I have been discussing
the situation for a while now.
And we both agreed that when
Edasaki got out of the hospital,
it would be best if the two of them lived together.
Aw, really?
Really. Of course, I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't going to miss Haru'ue.
Still. I think this is good.
They're close.
And they've been through so much together.
Besides, it's not like she's moving far away or anything.
And once the new term starts, we'll
still see each other at school every day.
Oh, yeah. You will, huh?
Good, then I guess I can stop worrying about you so much.
Yeah. Now please let go of my hair!
You're gonna be all right.
Yes.
Well, here I am!
So, how is it?
Perfect! It's totally cute!
It looks fantastic on you!
Aw, thank you!
Oh! So before, when you guys stayed behind
at the hospital to talk, this
is what you were talking about.
Mm-Hmm.
I couldn't wait to...
Go on, Sissy, you're up.
Oh, right. Here goes!
For you, Edasaki. To say "congratulations."
Congratulations!
Thanks so much!
So, are we ready to get going?
Huh? Where to?
A little celebration for you!
The place we reserved a table at has amazing cakes!
We get cake! That would be wonderful!
Hello, yes, this is Shirai.
Oh, hi Konori.
Eh? Traffic signal trouble?
Huh? Hey don't give me that look!
I didn't do it!
The signals in this area are down across the board.
I'm sorry to ask, but I need you now.
Yes. Right.
On my way as we speak.
Um. Uiharu's needed, too?
Of course I...
No. You can't go.
Edasaki is just getting released from the hospital.
I can cover this. You stay here-
What are you talking about?
I am a member of Judgment.
Please, start without us.
We'll be there as soon as we're done with this.
We'll see you later, then.
Good luck with those stoplights.
Thanks.
C'mon, let's go, Shirai.
Huh? Oh, right. Well, then.
They're gone!
Okay. We should get going, too.
It's not exactly how we planned it, but once again.
Congratulations, Edasaki!
Thank you so much!
That's delicious!
Isn't it?
Uiharu said if we were celebrating,
it absolutely had to be here,
and she handled everything
from the reservations to the cake!
Uiharu really is something else, isn't she?
Huh?
Before I was discharged,
she came to help me get moved and
take care of my school admission.
Didn't she?
Hm.
Yeah? That was nice of her.
Very nice!
I wonder if all Judgment officers are kind like her.
I'm glad we let Uiharu pick this place.
It's like she knew how much you would enjoy it.
I know, right?
This might be the best cake I've ever had!
Is that the key to your new place?
Mm-Hm.
Uiharu has been pretty helpful with all this, huh?
She was like this when it was my turn, too.
You mean, when the two of you were moving in together?
Yeah, that sounds like her.
Always the enthusiastic helper.
I was so nervous then, but Uiharu was there for me.
So now, it's my turn to help somebody else who needs it.
I'll be there to help Banri however I can,
just like Uiharu was there for me.
Of course.
Well, I just hope she gets here soon.
I'm sure she's giving it her all at work,
even as we speak.
Yeah, wearing an ugly helmet and
directing traffic or something, probably.
She could stand to ease up at a time like this, though.
But not being able to is what makes her, her.
You're right.
Maybe I should become a member of Judgment.
Huh?
Where'd that idea come from?
It's just a thought.
If I did join, maybe I would be more like Uiharu.
Heh.
You know, Edasaki.
I don't actually think that she was being nice to you
just because she's a member of Judgment.
Really? Then why?
Because she's your friend. Silly.
Yeah, you're right.
Ah, free from the hospital!
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
I know somebody else who was in there recently.
I was just wondering what it would've been like
for us to celebrate together like this when they got out.
You know?
Uhh...
Oh, sorry! Now I'm being silly.
Please forget I said anything! Really!
Well, whoever your friend is,
I hope they're feeling a lot better.
Yeah. So do I.
Good work today.
Sorry I had to call you out of the blue like that.
Stoplight trouble, of all things.
I was kinda' surprised.
There was some irregularity in the electrical system.
But in Academy City?
It's unusual for things like
that to happen here, you know.
There you are!
Oh, Uiharu, that's right.
Well, if we're all done here, we'll have to be...
Geez, what's gotten into you?
Hurry, there's some place I need you to take me!
Yes. Calm down, I know. Let's head ba...
No, not there!
I want you to take us somewhere else before that.
Huh?
Umm...
What do you think? Should we call them?
That might be a good idea.
Uh... Yeah. I'm calling them right now.
Hey, sorry to... keep you waiting.
Uh, me too.
Well, at least you made it!
Geez, it took you long enough.
Edasaki had to stop by the hospital, so she already left.
Oh! Really? She did? Shoot! I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
She wanted me to tell you thanks.
She had fun.
Um, here.
These are for you and Edasaki to share.
Huh?
Are those little cakes?
Oh, the thing is, Uiharu.
We actually already had cake while you were gone.
Well. Yes, I know that, but...
Having cake after cake is sorta...
No, you don't understa...
See, it's like I was trying to tell you.
Hey, now. It's really the thought that coun...
Listen, you guys-
They look just like they did before!
Huh?
You see, these are the same little cakes Uiharu
bought me once when I was nervous to make me feel better.
They were so delicious.
What's the matter, Haru'ue?
I'm hopeless!
I promised myself I wouldn't cry today!
Um, well.
Uiharu.
I want to be like you. So kind and considerate.
I want to help Banri like you helped me.
It'll be all right. You'll do fine, Haru'ue.
I know it. You can do this.
Thank you so much!
Now, now, calm down.
It's okay.
There's no reason to cry.
I mean...
And now there bawling like little babies.
Whatcha gonna do, huh?
It's so sweet.
Hey, you know.
I wonder how much of a help I actually was to Haru'ue.
Oh, don't be silly.
I think it's obvious that you were a big help.
Ow!
And not just to Haru'ue, either.
Edasaki, too.
I think you made a real difference in both their lives.
Thanks, Misaka.
Yeah, and you know, Sissy,
you make a real difference in my li... Ahh!
Well, let's head home!
Oh, I forgot.
I know of a shortcut up ahead.
Um, are you sure this is the right way?
Don't worry, okay? We just cut through here,
and we'll be on the main road in no time.
How many of these shortcuts do you know about?
What is it? Is something wrong, Sissy?
What is that down there?
Huh?
Hey, that looks like...
a little girl?
Huh?
Wow!
She's adorable!
Don't just stand there staring at her!
Hey, hold up, Kuroko!
She's opening her eyes.
Hi, sleepy head.
Why were you taking a nap in the park?
If you tell us your name, maybe we can help you.
Okay. Well, how old are you?
Can you tell us where you live?
Your school?
Your homeroom teacher's name, maybe?
This doesn't seem to be working.
Maybe she speaks a different language?
You guys are doing it wrong. Let me try.
When you're trying to talk to a little girl,
you need to get down to her eye level, like this.
Oh! That looks like some tasty candy!
Let's make a trade, okay?
My name is Ruiko. Now it's your turn.
Do you think you can tell me your name?
I'm Febri.
Aww...
That's a very pretty name!
Okay, then, Febri. What else can you tell us?
Anything goes. You can just pick something.
Mikoto Misaka.
Huh?
Huh? What?
The experiment was successful.
It was conducted to obtain data
regarding the fourth-ranked Level 5,
and the numbers came out more or less as predicted.
We ran into some unexpected complications on site,
but those ought to be resolved before much longer.
Everything is ready now.
The time has come to demonstrate our power.
We'll show this town of esper supremacists what we can do.
Those in favor of moving to the next phase of the project,
please raise your hands.
I want to know what the story is with this Febri girl.
Why does she know my name?
Maybe she's lost.
What should we do?
We will decide at the Academic Reach Assembly.
The Reach Assembly?