Amazing!
It's like a part of my body!
Like moving my own arms or legs!
All of this air is completely under my control!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
So fighting someone stronger
really was a shortcut to leveling up!
Guess they were right all along!
Thanks, third-string!
You served your purpose well,
and now I'm going to destroy you!
Huh?
How could this be happening now?
It looks like the plasma is diffusing.
Why is the wind suddenly acting like this?
It's not wind manipulation?
So, what?
The windmills are turning the wrong way.
Hold on.
I've heard about this before.
It's something about dynamo motors.
When they're hit by particular
electromagnetic waves, they...
Is it them?
Damn it. What do they think they're doing?
Those windmills aren't just spinning around haphazardly.
They're being directed to disrupt my formulas!
She's doing it!
The images she sees are going across the network!
I'm gonna' kill you!
I won't let you!
I don't understand you people.
First we have a gallant appearance from third-string.
And then you show up.
Just to defend this wind-up doll.
That's an overproduced, factory reject of yourself.
I would think, out of everyone in the world,
you would be the most disgusted by it.
Or maybe it freaks you out to see something
that looks like you getting all beat up.
But then, that's not a very good reason
to put your life on the line.
So maybe you just can't stand to have
somebody else become a Level 6 before you.
Or, maybe, it's some kind of atonement for being
the reason they started these
experiments in the first place.
I don't desire power for power's sake the way you do.
Nor do I think of this as atonement for any of the things
that I've done wrong in the past.
She's my sister.
All of these girls.
They are my little sisters.
That's why I'm here.
I'm sorry.
After all this time, I have no right to ask you this,
but still...
Just this one time, may I fulfill my role as big sister?
Yes.
Heh.
I will not let another one of them die!
Huh?
Man, that's rich!
I have to admit that I didn't see that one coming.
Playing at sisters? That's a good one!
You're way out of your league here.
If there's something I wanna do, you can't stop me.
Two little girls like you can't even slow me down.
It's kind of like how a person's
vision can only be measured up to 20/20.
Level 5 is the highest rank an
esper can attain in Academy City.
So that's where I'm stuck, even
though I'm better than the rest of you.
I'm sick of looking at the same damn face day after day,
so I'm gonna kill all...
Impossible.
Doesn't he get it?
I'm the most experienced killer this city's ever seen.
I know so much about what it takes to destroy a person,
I'm almost sick of it.
He's standing.
He shouldn't even... be alive.
What am I doing?
This idiot just doesn't know when to quit.
Sure, I lost control of the wind.
But I can still finish him off.
All I need is one touch.
This really has been fascinating.
But I've had enough.
It ends now!
You're the strongest guy in Academy City.
That's not gonna help you now.
The weakest guy is taking you down.
I don't get it.
Why can't I break this guy?
He's protecting them. The wind-up dolls.
I was one step away from it. From absolute power.
And now. And now.
What if having too much power,
turns the world itself against me?
Ultimately resulting in
destruction, rather than protection.
Just think.
If you were to gain even greater power than you have.
Then what would your life be like?
Just do the experiments,
you have nothing to lose.
It's not like any people will get hurt.
Guinea pigs. Wind-up dolls. Clones.
It's not like I'm seeking immortality.
I just want to gather enough power
that nobody will ever want to fight me again.
If that happens.
Then someday, maybe.
If that happens, then.
Then, no one will.
So many Sisters, living the best that they can.
All of these girls.
They're my sisters.
Really.
What am I even doing anymore?
Hi. Are, are you?
Just thought I would drop by.
Oh, guess he's asleep.
To think he actually defeated the
first-ranked esper in Academy City.
You must be crazy or something.
You know that?
Uh... Sorry. Did I wake you?
Uh. Here! Get well soon!
I picked the most expensive cookies the store had.
For the price, I'm guessing they're pretty good.
I just thought...
I really ought to try and do something to,
you know, say thank...
When it comes to cookies...
Don't people say homemade are the best?
Huh?
Heh, heh. Is that so?
Can you seriously picture me baking cookies?
No, never.
I'm pretty sure if you tried to the cookies
would come out all misshapen and disgusting.
It would be ugly for sure.
I meant that baking's not my
style, not that I can't do it!
Hey, calm down! I'm injured, here!
Or you're gonna fry all the hospital's fancy equipment
if you're not careful!
Okay, fine.
So, uh.
Your sister stopped by.
She said the experiments are over.
Mmm.
They're over, but because of me so many...
Well, you know, if you hadn't offered them your
DNA map, none of the sisters would ever have existed.
That experiment was messed up in a lot of ways,
but at least there was something good that came from it.
Your sisters.
You can take pride in that.
Think about it this way.
If it weren't for you,
they wouldn't have had a chance at life whatsoever.
What's the point in moping?
I don't think they'd like to see you like this.
Beating yourself up.
What should we play on?
How are your injuries doing?
These are really nothing serious
compared to what happened to that boy.
Good. I'm glad.
Here we go. Whee!
Ha, ha, ha! Yay!
Lives created by a machine.
They're born without knowledge of the world.
Blank slates.
So it's not surprising that when they
are told they're nothing but lab rats.
they swiftly come to accept it as the simple truth.
However, if they're given the chance
to look at the world around them.
Like she did.
Then surely, they can...
So, listen, um.
You probably can't forgive what I did.
I doubt you even want to see my face.
But, uh. I do think you might have some trouble,
you know, adjusting to a normal life. So, if, um...
If there's anything at all I can do to, uh, help?
"This is called 'stand and swing'," Says Misaka,
putting into practice knowledge she gained
from Testament and showing off her skills.
Wow!
That's amazing!
"Done. Any more of that and I risk
aggravating my injuries, so that's all for me.
Whew!" says Misaka, growing tired.
"What? Is something the matter?"
Sorry, just give me a moment.
Come on, Sis!
Let's do it again!
No. I think that's enough.
"No, it isn't."
"As the big sister, it is your
obligation to indulge your younger sister."
Huh?
Says Misaka to the impressionable
youngster, hoping to brainwash her.
Hey, you!
Cute, yes?
It is what people call a kitten.
I know that!
Hey, are you and this other lady sisters?
You look the same!
Uh...
You've got to be twins, right?
So who's the older sister and who's the younger sister?
Uh...
Well, the thing is...
Ah! Hold on, hold on! I wanna guess!
Okay, let's see. I think...
Hm...
You were the one who wanted to guess.
It's you!
You're the younger sister! You've gotta be!
I mean, you've got a Gekota.
Uh...
I like stuffed animals, too!
Huh?
"Mmph!" says Misaka, indicating stifled laughter.
It cannot be denied.
Her tastes are inappropriate for her age.
She is rude, hot-tempered, and belligerent.
She is sensitive, easily embarrassed,
and even more easily offended.
However, this problematic older
sister of mine risked her life for me.
Huh?
It is strange.
After last night's experiment,
Misaka was supposed to be dead.
It was supposed to play out as it always had,
more than ten thousand times before.
The same course of events.
And yet, here I am.
Misaka is still alive.
Still walking and talking.
The Misakas were disposable.
We were created in order to be killed.
That was the sole purpose for our existence.
The reason for which we were born.
And now, thanks to you and that boy,
we have lost our purpose.
We are unemployed.
Huh?
We are lost.
Adrift in a world that makes little sense.
So, please.
"Help Misaka.
Stay with her while she goes on her search.
While she tries to discover a
new meaning for this life of hers."
Says Misaka, asking her big
sister for a world of indulgence.
Yes. I'd love to.
Do it again, Sis!
Okay, okay. Ready?
Uh-huh!
That's all she said?
So she didn't give you any details then?
No. None.
Misaka baking. Huh.
She said she wanted to get away from
all the prying eyes in the dorm kitchen,
so she asked to borrow my oven instead.
It seemed like a really big deal.
I almost don't believe it.
Pigs must be flying now.
Yeah, right?
Still. I'm glad.
She seems more cheerful than she's been in a while.
I agree.
I wish we knew who she was making the present for, though.
I asked a million times, but she wouldn't give up a name.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Jeez. Saten got a little too much
enjoyment out of the whole thing.
After all, it's not like this
is supposed to mean something.
It's a thank-you. That's it.
Of course, this is him we're talking about.
"I was only fighting for my own sake.
I've done nothing that deserves any thanks."
I'll bet that's what he says.
Maybe I'm just being childish.
No, no, no! Anyway, whether he wants thanks or
not, I still need to show him proper gratitude.
U... Uh...
I went to all the trouble of making these things,
and if he doesn't accept them,
then he's going to pay for...
What's he gonna pay for?
Huh?
What are you doing all the way out here?
You're still supposed to be in the hospital!
Well, uh...
hospitals aren't exactly cheap.
And I have a hungry roommate who gets even
more violent every day that I'm away from home.
Huh?
Hey.
For that matter, what are you doing way out here?
Uh.
Well, I...
Oh, I know.
You must've been coming to visit me again.
Hah! Yeah, right.
I... I was not!
Wow, uh. you don't have to deny it so forcefully.
Idiot!
Uh, no, I wasn't coming out here to check on you.
It's just that, lately, you've helped me out an awful lot.
I... I, uh, didn't... mean to.
I just, wanted to.
Look, ants!
Ants?
Oh. You have a research project or something?
Some summer vacation homework?
"Look, ants!" What am I, five years old?
Sorry to interrupt you.
See ya around, zapper.
Mikoto Misaka!
What?
I have an actual name!
It's Mikoto Misaka. It isn't Zapper.
You always call me that.
Try using my real name sometime!
Then again, maybe that's just too much to ask of you.
See you later, Misaka.
I've got bad news!
Listen, Sis...
What happened? What's the matter with you?
Ah! Are you feeling okay?
Are you hurt somewhere?
Did you eat something that didn't agree with you?
What? What are you talking about?
And what's this bad news you mentioned?
Oh, about that.
The head resident seems to have learned about the nights
you've been away from the dorms without permission.
She says you'd better have a very
good explanation for your absence.
That's bad, huh?
I'm gonna need an excuse.
Wait... you came all the way
out here just to tell me that?
Thank you.
But how did you know where I was?
Huh? As they say, "like calls to like."
Wherever Sissy is, there too will be Kuroko.
But more importantly, are you sure everything is okay?
Because if anything were to happen to you, Sissy,
I wouldn't rest until I had done everything tha...
Honestly.
Keep talking crazy and I'll leave you here.
Can you really blame me, Sissy?
There was a look on your face
that I've never seen there before.
I'm so glad Misaka's feeling better now!
I still want to know who those cookies were for!
Exposed!
Uh, Shirai?
It's time to come out of your shell, Sissy.
Body and soul!