♪
♪ Robin
♪ Deep in their forest
hideaway ♪
♪ The outlaws have made
their getaway ♪
♪ From the sheriff
and his men ♪
♪ Their philosophy on life
is to live and rob again ♪
♪ Then to give it
to the poor ♪
♪ Come along if you can to join
our merry band ♪
♪ Robin, ride on
and never lose ♪
♪ Robin, good luck to you
♪ Robin of the forest
♪ God save the king
♪ And God help the poor
♪ If anyone can save us
♪ Of this you can be sure
♪ Robin, ride on
and never lose ♪
♪ Robin, good luck to you
♪ Robin of the forest
♪
Oh, where am I?
What happened?
Where is this place?
It, it seem familiar
but I don't know.
Oh, I'm so confused.
Yes.
I remember.
My knight.
I was going to be attacked
by wolves.
Oh, oh, ohh, ohh!
Oh!
That knight, he saved me.
I wonder where he is now.
Mmm, mmm.
Oh!
Who are you?
What do you want?
Ohh, oh.
Do not be afraid, my lady
I mean you no harm.
It is me.
Huh?
Oh, my knight.
He's so tall
and strong
and handsome.
Oh, why does he stare at me so?
He saved my life but there's
something about his eyes.
♪
Good sir knight,
I would like to thank you
for saving my life yesterday
Here.
Sweet lady,
it was my duty,
but what was a lady
of such obvious nobility
doing in such a wild and
dangerous place all alone?
Oh, I can't say.
Ah, oh.
Oh.
There is no need for you to
answer that.
After all, everybody has secrets
they'd rather keep from others.
Oh.
Ha, ha.
Including myself.
Mmm.
I know what your family name is.
It's Huntington isn't it, Robin?
Huh?
How do you know my name?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
I know everything!
I'm the wisest man
in Sherwood Forest.
I could tell you things about
the place no other man alive
could tell you.
Like that bow you've got.
It has a special kind of magic
attached to it.
This bow has magic powers?
Mm-hmm.
Any man with evil thoughts,
corrupted soul, or impure heart
will never,
never by God's will,
manage to draw this bow!
What?
Friar Tuck,
what are you talkin' about?
It's true.
No one of impure heart.
Only men of the strongest virtue
can use this bow, my friend.
I never knew that.
Well, no one can know
everything, except me of course.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hmm, what's this?
Well with a heart as pure and
virtuous as yours, Friar Tuck,
I was hopin' that you'd be able
to show me how to do it,
unless you're not
strong enough, Friar?
Hmm.
Oh.
I'll do it!
Let me have that bow here!
Mmm.
Now I'll show you what a simple
friar can do, Robin.
Now.
(groaning)
♪
Oh, I don't believe it!
Eh, hey, how am I doin'?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Okay, okay.
You've proved your point.
♪
No.
Oh, oh, oh.
Everything's gone.
Our home completely destroyed!
I'll never forget that night!
(shouting)
♪
I promise you, father,
the Huntington family
will survive.
I'll make them pay for this!
(owl hooting)
He came this way.
I know it.
Wait.
What have we here?
This looks like&
Yes.
It's one of his.
I'd know that arrowhead
anywhere.
The same kind of arrow
that scarred my cheek.
Uh!
(thunder)
♪
If only I could find something,
something to remind me.
♪
Father!
His portrait!
Is that all I have left of you?
My father.
Come on, Robin, up you go now.
Hold on.
Pull back with
all your strength.
That's it.
Keep the other arm straight.
Good.
I told you not to do it.
You have to learn your lesson.
Now stop crying.
Come on.
I'll sure you how to ride, okay?
Hi yah!
Come on!
Let's go!
♪
They can destroy our home,
but they can't destroy our name!
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Huh?
Who is it?
Who's there?
Come on out!
Robin Huntington.
Oh.
Gilbert!
So, we meet again,
my young friend.
I think we have
unfinished business.
How could I ever forget?
Ah hah.
Gilbert.
♪
Are you looking for me,
Huntington, or your father?
Hah!
Come on, boy!
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
Must be brave!
This is it, Huntington!
This is where you die!
♪
Ah.
Hah!
♪
Huh?
Ah.
Hmm.
Huntington!
Ahh!
(rocks falling)
♪
We will meet again, Huntington.
Nobody cuts me and lives.
I'm going to kill you, Robin,
but before I do,
I will give you a chance
to see if you can kill me.
Gilbert!
Well here I am boy!
Just draw your bow if you can.
Alright!
You got lucky once,
the result of which
I will carry with me forever.
You will pay for that.
(thunder)
Alright!
We'll see who's gonna pay
for what!
♪
Come on, bow.
Don't let me down now.
Now if I just get him
in my sights.
Now!
♪
Ah, ha, ha!
Huh?
You missed me, boy.
Now it's my turn.
Prepare to die!
Ha, ha, ha.
There is no way out for you,
Huntington, no where to hide.
♪
Get ready to join your father!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well what are you waiting for?
Do it!
Take it!
Whah?
Hmm.
Well, pick it up!
Huh?
I am no coward, and I will not
fight against an unarmed man.
Pick it up, and may God grant me
the power to strike you down,
that is,
unless you are afraid of me,
Robin?
I'm no coward!
Then pick it up!
Hah!
This time, to the death!
♪
Gilbert!
Turn around and face me, coward!
You're no match for me.
Go now, while you still can.
My code of honor will not
allow me to kill a weakling.
Ohh, ohh, help!
Help me!
Ohh!
Oh, if only that brave and
handsome knight were here,
he would help me.
I wonder what he's doing now
and if he thinks of me?
♪
Not bad for a boy.
What's the matter?
Getting heavy?
No way!
♪
I'm fighting for
my family's honor!
♪
Got you!
Ahh!
Help!
Huh?
Oh!
Help me!
Help me please!
Oh!
Come on!
Help me!
Help me please!
Gotcha!
Hold on tight now,
Marian I'll pull you up.
Oh, Will.
Huh, uh.
Oh, phew.
Thanks a lot, Will.
But what are you doing up here
all alone?
Oh, I lost something
that's very dear to me,
a special golden cross that
belongs to my family.
Huh?
You lost a golden cross?
Yes.
It's the golden cross of
Lancaster.
It's the family heirloom
which proves I'm nobility.
And you think you
lost it around here?
I don't know.
The cross belonged
to my mother,
and without it Baron Alwine
will never recognize me
as a Lancaster.
Oh!
Hmm.
I have to get it back.
It was my mother's
most prized possession.
Ow,
ohh!
Huntington's bow.
Ow!
The very same weapon
that scarred me.
Don't touch it!
Gilbert, do you hear me?
Your father's bow.
♪
How ironic that you should die
by an arrow that was shot from
your father's bow.
Yes.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Say goodbye, Robin.
Hmm?
Uh, uh, I&
Huh?
I can't draw it.
Oh, come on you stupid bow!
Ah, oh.
Friar Tuck.
Any man with evil thoughts,
corrupted soul, or impure heart
will never, by God's will,
manage to draw this bow.
Ah, I can't.
Hah!
Ohh!
♪
Trapped like a rat.
Well, well.
Huh?
Oh, ah.
Ow!
Oh, uh!
I'm not prepared to slay
a wounded enemy.
But his father&
Huh?
Father!
♪
No!
Father!
Oh, Father, Father.
Gilbert, come back and fight!
I will leave you with
your humiliation, Robin,
but I shall return.
As darkness and the rain fell
on the ruined castle,
Gilbert walked away
into the night,
leaving Robin all alone,
trapped beneath
the wooden beams
of his former home.
♪
Baron Alwine,
what are your plans?
We sent our soldiers against
the outlaws but got nowhere,
then we recruited mercenaries
with terrible results.
Now, how much will it cost us to
get rid of this gal?
Oh, a few sovereigns.
Stop complaining, Bishop.
Oh?
I was going to lend you
the money for you to marry
the Lancaster girl
on one condition,
that you act now to do away
with these criminals!
Otherwise, they'll be nothing
but trouble!
I've an idea.
To capture Marian
and bring her to the castle
is not so much
a question of force
as of cunning, Baron.
Now surely you have a soldier
who is very loyal to you,
a special knight
of exceptional talent?
Gilbert you mean?
You want me to kidnap the girl?
Call it what you like.
Just take her
and bring her here.
Her name's Marian.
You'll know her
by the golden cross she wears.
I refuse to do it!
What?
This is not a job for
an honorable knight like me.
In fact, such a mission
is more in your line.
What are you saying?
Uh-oh.
♪
Gilbert, listen to me.
Fetch me the girl's cross.
Do you understand?
Why I--
Gilbert, remember.
I remember.
A true knight serves his lord
all his life,
and to whom did you swear
eternal loyalty?
To you.
Yes, you did.
And who was it
who saved your life
and the life of your sister?
Hmm?
You, Baron Alwine.
Then let's not waste
any more time.
Go, knight, and do your duty.
I swear by my sword&
Hi, Marian.
I'm looking for Robin.
Do you know where he is?
He's gone to the head
of the river.
Oh right.
Oh, hey&
Huh?
Thank you, Will.
Hi.
Hey, Marian, what's up with you?
I've been thinking.
I must go to Nottingham and
give myself up to Baron Alwine.
But, Marian,
what about your cross?
Well what can I do?
The cross of the Lancasters
is gone forever.
Anyway, I just came to say
goodbye and to say thank you
for looking after me so well.
Mmm, sorry, Robin, I have to go.
Marian, are you sure?
Look, none of here
want you to go,
but if you don't wanna stay,
well go!
It's my fate, Robin.
Well I believe you can control
your own destiny, Marian!
If you stay here
in the forest,
I'll protect you
from the Baron Alwine!
Oh, Robin, I wish I could stay
here in Sherwood Forest forever,
but I made a pledge
to my family
that I would go
to Baron Alwine's castle.
♪
Hey, shut up, will ya?
I wonder how the Chief's doing?
You know, Jenny, he's never
talked to a girl alone
before now.
But why does he wanna be on his
own with Winifred?
What's the big secret?
Shh, be quiet!
We don't want them to hear us!
Oh.
What is it you want with us?
Well, listen.
This, this, this gift
is for you!
Oh.
Ahh!
Nope, this is the real gift.
Oh, it's gorgeous!
Ah, oh, really?
Try it on.
It'll look great on you!
Oh, no.
It could be Marian's cross.
Well I got it in the woods,
well sort of found it.
Ah, yeah, well, never mind.
Go on then.
Try it.
Oh, ah.
It looks fantastic.
You think so?
Yeah, yeah!
You look like a princess.
Oh, oh, how gorgeous!
Mmm, ah, um, ah,
I picked 'em especially&
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, uh&
Hey, Chief, we need ya!
Oh, this better be important!
Ah, excuse me, okay?
I'll be back in a minute.
Don't go away.
Oh.
Ahh!
Oh, Jenny, you rat!
You spied on us!
♪
The cross.
Found you.
Hah!
Oh!
Ah!
I've got you!
Ohh!
Help,
help!
Wait up!
It's all Winifred's fault.
Little John gave her a cross
and she knew it was Marian's
but she didn't
give it back to her.
You found my cross?
No!
If Winifred
was wearing my cross,
she would've been
mistaken for me.
And Gilbert
was supposed to kidnap me!
♪
(laughter)
At last it's mine,
the Lancaster cross.
I have waited so long
to hold this in my hand.
Congratulations, Gilbert,
you are a loyal servant.
So this is the famous Marian.
She is just as pretty
as people say.
But you are slightly younger
than I thought, huh?
I'm not Marian!
Speak up for an old man, dear.
You're making a big mistake!
I'm not Marian!
Huh?
What does she mean?
You told me, Baron, that
Marian would be recognizable
by her cross.
This girl had the cross and so
I bought her to you, my lord.
What?
You may go.
Wh--, what?
Do stop whatting, Bishop.
Gilbert has done his job well.
I have what I need,
the cross of Lancaster.
♪
Goodbye, Robin.
But, Marian&
Don't try, Robin.
If we resist,
we'll put Marian in danger.
Marian, stop!
Captain, will you lead me
to the castle
and tell Baron Alwine
I am here?
Don't go!
Marian!
Robin, thank you for
the wonderful moments
you've given me.
I will never forget the happy
days spent in Sherwood Forest
with you.
Never!
Don't forget me.
♪
Oh.
Marian!
Marian, don't go.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
We were beginning to think
you wouldn't come,
but better late than never.
Marian Lancaster,
welcome to my little home.
Have you two met?
So this is the real Marian?
Look, even prettier
than I imagined,
and now we've got you
all to ourselves.
What fun.
Oh.
Ah, oh, Marian, Marian!
Winifred!
Oh, I've been so scared here!
Winifred,
it's all gonna be okay.
You'll be alright
now that I'm here.
There's nothing to worry about.
You'll soon be free
to join Robin
and the others in the forest.
But what about you?
Don't you worry about me.
Will and Robin are outside
waiting for you.
What did you just say?
Huh?
Will and Robin.
I distinctly heard their names.
So?
Which means that
Winifred is another of
the Huntington family.
Ah!
Oh, you're not going anywhere,
Huntington.
Guards, take this girl
to the dungeon!
Ahh, Marian!
Let her go!
Marian, help me!
What are you doing to her?
It's me you want.
Let her go,
let her go!
Can you imagine
that I was going to release
one of the Huntingtons?
Thank you for your help, Marian.
(laughter)
♪
Marian, here, but why?
As soon as we've finished here,
that cross will be mine,
and with it I'll be able
to discover
the secret hiding place of
the treasure of the Lancasters.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Marian, your head.
Yes.
All that Lancaster treasure,
diamonds, rubies,
everything I could want.
With the crown I pronounce thee,
Marian Lancaster,
goddaughter to our dear
Bishop Hartford,
and may this union
make us all very, very happy.
No!
I'll see you dead before I let
that happen!
Oh!
Die!
♪
Marian!
Yah!
Hey!
Get him, get him!
Marian!
Aaahh!
♪
That's too bad.
You'll have to do better
than that to kill me.
But that's not the sort of
behavior one expects
from a dutiful
goddaughter, is it?
♪
Baron, be careful!
She'll break.
♪
Marian!
Now come along, Marian.
It's getting ridiculous
getting upset
over a little thing like this,
don't you think?
Yes, my dear, let's just get on
with the ceremony, shall we?
♪
Oh, Father.
Robin!
Come along, girl.
No.
I won't let you
get your hands on me.
Huh?
I'd rather die first.
Ah, oh.
Oh.
Wait!
Think about what you are doing,
child!
I've thought about it
long and hard,
and this is the only way out.
I'd kill myself before
I'd bow to you, Alwine.
I'll show you how
a Lancaster can die.
Big deal.
You can't!
It's a sin against God!
Oh!
If you are to die, Marian,
you won't be alone!
Marian, we will die with honor
as Lancasters should.
Mmm.
We love you, Marian!
Oh, be brave.
Hah!
♪
Marian!
You miserable bunch,
go and stop her!
Now!
Come on!
Yah!
Right.
This is it.
Go on, Marian, do it.
Goodbye, Robin.
♪
Marian!
Robin!
♪
Oh, oh, Robin.
Oh, Robin!
Marian!
Stay where you are.
I've got a surprise.
You animal!
Robin!
Save yourself!
Stay calm!
It's gonna be alright!
Let 'em go, Alwine!
I know you're not too bright,
boy,
but I though that even you might
understand why I can't do that.
I do, however,
insist that you join them.
Yes, join then in jail.
Never!
Marian!
Ohh!
Help!
Let her go!
Be quiet!
That is unless you want to see
your friends' blood.
♪
Robin, behind you!
Huh?
Gilbert!
Excuse my intrusion, Bishop.
Now, Robin, fight me
like a man and die like one.
Ahh!
♪
Oh, oh, stop it!
Come, not even you could
stop this fight.
They hate each other!
Now brave, Sir Gilbert, kill
this rash and vicious intruder.
♪
Watch carefully, lords.
This is an historic occasion.
The brave, noble,
honest Sir Gilbert
will avenge himself in battle
against the criminal,
Robin Huntington,
who will be seeing his father
much sooner
than he expected.
♪
Nice trick, Gilbert.
Well that was fun.
Ahh!
Ah!
Oh!
Prepare yourself, Robin!
It's time to die!
No, wait!
No!
Marian.
♪
Oh, ah.
Huh?
Hmm.
I don't believe it.
(laughing)
This is really some joke.
The one person I hate saved by
the one person I love
and will now never love me.
What have I done
to deserve this?
Why are the fates
so cruel to me?
A blood thirsty coward.
What?
No!
Don't!
It was wrong of me
to suppose
you could have
been anything else.
Robin's friends have
been captured by the Baron
and are being
held hostage by him.
They'll die if
he tries to fight you!
They are hostages?
What are you waiting for,
Gilbert?
Finish him off, Gilbert!
Now I see.
The whole thing was
a set up for me.
Oh!
Ah hah!
My Lord Bishop, Baron Alwine,
I am a man of honor
and I cannot take advantage
of this situation.
You'll do as I say!
You made me look stupid,
but worse than that,
you tried to make me look like
a coward and a cheat.
Excuse me.
Ah, ah!
Oh!
You'll pay for that, Gilbert!
If she is going to be
my goddaughter,
we have to crown her!
No, just get the cross!
Marian!
Here,
Robin!
Well that's a load off my
skirts.
Hey!
This one's for you, Marian.
♪
Huh?
Oh, oh, no, no,
ah, ah!
Ah!
(chandelier crashing)
(screaming)
♪
Robin!
Huh?
Marian!
♪
How are you?
Okay.
You mongrel!
Glad to see you're
still in charge, Baron.
Now both of you listen to me.
Marian and I will now return
to live in Sherwood Forest.
To you, Robin of Huntington,
I give my daughter.
Look after her well.
Just remember, Alwine, whenever
you send your guards after me,
I'll be
ready for 'em.
(glass breaking)
♪
Ha, ha, ha.
So, Baron,
today we execute Gilbert.
He deserves to die very
painfully considering the depth
of his disgrace
and dishonor.
How shall we do it, Baron?
I will be delighted to assist.
Calm down, Bishop,
and look at this letter.
Hmm.
Why look, a letter to Gilbert
from his sister, Cleo.
What a fool she is.
Doesn't she know of Gilbert's
shameful disobedience
of my orders?
Huh.
\"My dear brother, I hope
this letter finds you well.\"
Thanks to your brother, I've
lost a beautiful goddaughter!
He's ruined me!
He's being very stubborn.
He does nothing to save himself
from execution.
So let's execute him
immediately!
No.
I'll give him one last chance.
If he publicly repents
his disobedience and swears
eternal loyalty
to me once more,
I shall suspend
the execution.
You're being rash, Baron.
He could be disloyal again.
I'm sure he does
not deserve mercy.
But I can still use him.
It would be a waste
to execute him now.
We must go and see
if he is willing.
Hmm.
Baron Alwine!
Yes?
Gi--, Gilbert has escaped, sir!
What?
Where is Gilbert?
(horse neighing)
Baron, do something
before he escapes!
Is he there?
Yes,
look!
He's about to leave the castle!
I've never seen such impudence!
You'll regret this, Gilbert!
I'll take care of you myself,
Gilbert!
♪
Huh?
You fool!
You didn't think I'd let you
live did you?
Huh?
Ah, hmm.
Ah!
That's Little John.
♪
Try me again.
Come on, Marian.
That's it!
Come on, come on, lift it!
♪
Huh?
Marian.
♪
Free of that Baron at last,
but now I have some business
to settle.
Alright, my friend,
nearly there.
♪
Are you worried about
what happened back there?
It's okay.
We'll be fine.
You know, we still have
our mission to accomplish.
♪
Come, my friend, to the woods!
Hurry!
Marian asked us to help her.
She wants to learn how to fight
with a sword.
So, we're teaching her.
Right, men?
Marian, is this true?
Yes.
Of course, she had to pay us.
We don't work for free.
See this?
She gave us her dress.
Actually, I wanted
that pretty little cross
she wears 'round her neck.
But she wouldn't give it up.
Marian,
please give me the sword.
But we can't just give up.
We'll never give up, Marian.
I promise you,
but we can't do it by force.
Huh?
Did you hear that?
It must be the soldiers!
They found us!
Get ready!
Here they come!
We'll be ready!
Look,
there's only one man!
Careful.
It could be a trap.
Who is it?
Little John and his pathetic
band of outlaws.
So this is where you are hiding.
Huh?
Gilbert?
It's Gilbert!
Huh?
Marian, what have they
done to you?
Dressed her like an outlaw.
I must take her away from here.
Living in the forest
like a wild animal.
She deserves better than this.
So, it's Alwine's pet poodle.
You better get outta here.
Not going, huh?
Well you've had your chance.
Prepare to fight!
♪
(muttering)
I'll take that.
Ah, huh?
Outta my way, Huntington.
Keep away, Gilbert!
Look out!
♪
She's afraid of me.
You have no need of this now.
A princess should not
lay hands on a sword.
Marian!
Forgive me.
He's taken Marian!
After him!
Let me go!
You only came to take me to
Alwine and Hartford
at Nottingham Castle,
didn't you?
No.
Things are different now.
Alwine is no longer my master.
What?
I have left the castle.
I serve no one.
I am a masterless knight.
At last I am free
to do as I please.
Oh, but, how?
Oh.
Fear not, Marian,
you are with me now!
Marian!
Hold on, Marian!
I'm coming!
Someone approaches.
They will not take her
from me again.
♪
Marian!
Marian, do not be afraid.
I will protect you.
Prepare to die,
Huntington!
Ah!
♪
Robin!
Gilbert!
♪
This is hopeless, Much.
We'll never find them
in this place.
Forget the dress.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Give up?
That dress is our loot,
and what about Robin?
We can't go on!
There's too much mist!
Are you tryin' to tell me
Little John
is afraid of a bit of mist?
It's not the mist
that scares me.
Not the mist?
♪
Stop!
Please stop!
Huh?
You mustn't fight.
Ah, Robin, Gilbert no longer
serves Baron Alwine.
What?
What do you mean?
Ah!
What's the matter, Huntington?
Why do you stop?
I cannot fight you, Gilbert.
What do you mean?
Fight!
No.
If you no longer serve
Baron Alwine, I cannot.
You are a fool, Robin!
And this is my answer!
Robin!
Ah!
Robin, don't!
Father.
Robin!
What's this?
He does not move.
He does not flinch from death.
He is willing to die for
his principles, for Marian!
♪
I cannot.
Oh.
Oh!
Ah, ah.
It's over, Gilbert.
Ahh!
♪
Hold on, Much!
Well, whoa, what's happening
to us, Little John?
I told you there was
something to be afraid of,
and here it comes now.
Look out!
Ohh!
♪
Robin!
Marian!
Ahh!
Marian and Gilbert!
♪
Marian, Gilbert.
Marian!
Oh!
You've been hit by an arrow.
You fool!
You didn't think
I'd let you live did you?
Ah, ah.
Gilbert, let me go
or we'll both fall.
Gilbert, you must not
die for me.
(rocks creaking)
♪
Robin!
No, Robin.
Come, Gilbert!
You must hold on to me!
Ah, uh, uh.
Gilbert, gimme your hand!
(rocks creaking)
Ahh!
Gilbert, you must let go of me!
Quickly!
Gilbert, give me your hand!
♪
This Robin of Huntington
has shown much bravery.
♪
And now you, my sweet Marian,
you would die to save me.
♪
Oh, Marian, my love.
Gilbert.
(rocks creaking)
Ah, hah!
♪
(rocks creaking)
(heartbeats)
Oh, ah.
Marian.
Gilbert!
(wind blowing)
We're almost there.
Down there.
Look.
That's Nottingham.
Hah, huh, huh.
Hey, stop!
Hey, come back!
Hey!
Whoa!
Ah!
Oh!
Come on, guys,
keep up.
Get him!
Come on,
after him!
I'll kill him personally.
♪
Huh?
They're Baron Alwine's men.
I'm surrounded!
♪
Better move!
Huh?
Ahh!
♪
There's no escape.
Baron Alwine
has ordered us to kill you,
and he didn't want anyone
to see it being done.
Grr.
Ah!
♪
Stop!
Huh?
Hey who are you, huh?
Mind your own business.
Get outta here!
You leave that poor,
defenseless girl alone!
Do not be afraid.
Oh.
She's beautiful!
♪
I'm from Cockley Nunnery.
My name is Cleo.
I'm a student over there.
You three men should be
ashamed of yourselves
for such a cowardly,
underhand attack.
Umm.
Forgive us, sister, please.
We, ah, come on.
You're safe now.
Ow, oh.
Oh, have you been hurt?
Let me have a look at it.
Please let me.
No, it's okay
You're hurt.
Let me see.
No, I'm, I'm fine.
Oh.
Please don't scream.
I, I had to dress up
to escape from some men
that were chasing me.
Oh, oh.
I must apologize for the way
that I reacted back there.
You see, I was brought up
in a convent
and it's the only life
I've ever really known.
I'd never mixed with the outside
world and never spoken to a boy.
♪
Uh, well, ah, well, ah,
my name is
Robert Huntington,
but everyone
calls me Robin.
Robin, a nice name.
And what should I call you?
Just Cleo will be fine, Robin.
Hmm.
Well, Cleo, what is it that
brings you to Nottingham?
It must be pretty serious
to keep you away from school.
Ah, ah, I will not be
going back to school ever.
Huh?
♪
I received some terrible news
only recently.
It was news about my brother.
He was murdered.
(sobbing)
Cleo, I'm sorry.
♪
Oh, my poor brother.
Robin.
♪
The next morning they walked
down to the river together.
♪
This is where we must part.
Take care of yourself, Robin.
Thank you for all
you've done for me, Cleo.
What's this?
It's something I want you
to wear.
For me?
Yes, for you.
It's a good luck charm.
I made it myself.
If you wear it, it will protect
you from danger.
It's beautiful, Cleo.
I wish I had something
to give you.
Oh, it's okay.
Hey, I've got it!
Why don't you play that tune?
It was so beautiful!
My father taught me how to get
a tune out of these leaves
when I was
only a child.
He also taught me
that beautiful song.
Your father sounds
like a wonderful man, Robin.
He was.
My father's dead.
Oh, Robin, I'm sorry!
Hey, don't worry!
You just listen.
♪
The two of them stood there
on the bridge
listening to
the wonderful music.
Neither of them wanted to leave
the other, but they had to.
All Robin could do was hope
he would see her again.
♪
Ah!
Look out, lady,
you'll be crushed!
Ah, get him!
Get back!
Watch out!
Did you see that?
Sure did.
Now what a horse!
There boy.
It's okay.
There.
Well, who is that girl?
Huh?
What's she doing?
Greetings, Baron Alwine.
I'm very pleased to see you.
♪
Ah, hey, Cleo!
Hey!
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, Cleo, I must see you again!
♪
Huh?
Who's there?
(laughter)
Oh, it's you two.
Are you okay, Robin?
You look kinda strange.
Ah, I thought you'd gone back
to the forest.
Well we decided this mornin'
to tame it in the city.
Hmm.
Robin, you sure
there's nothing wrong?
You look like you're in a daze
or something.
Hah!
That's nonsense!
Oh, I get it.
Robin's fallen in love.
Ah, don't be ridiculous.
Okay, okay,
have it your own way.
I was gonna give you
the benefit of my expertise
in affairs of the heart
but it doesn't matter.
You obviously have no need
of my services.
Oh, Much, you're an idiot!
I'll never trust you again
whatever happens!
♪
No.
It's impossible.
Oh, Cleo!
Oh, I just hope
I'm not dreaming.
Cleo!
My brother, murdered.
Yes, murdered.
The noble Sir Gilbert
was assassinated.
But who could've committed
such a terrible crime?
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Cleo!
♪
My dear brother, Gilbert.
This was your room.
The room where you
wrote those letters to me
that I was so happy to receive,
that I opened with
this little knife.
Letters I will never
receive again.
♪
Cleo!
Oh, Cleo, I'm so&
Huh?
Ah!
♪
No!
Oh, Robin, I came here
to avenge my brother,
Gilbert's death,
and now I have done so.
Huh?
Gilbert?
Then you are his sister!
♪
That's right, and Gilbert,
the most wonderful brother
anyone could have,
is dead.
I didn't know.
♪
Uh.
This lucky charm you gave me.
It saved my life.
Robin,
I thought I was
in love with you
and my cross saved your life.
♪
Robin!
Listen to me, Cleo.
Alwine cheated you
to use you against me.
Your brother is&
Huh?
Look out, Cleo!
Ah!
Ms. Cleo.
Who are you?
We are knights belonging to
the order of the Black Rose.
We were grooms to your brother,
Gilbert.
We received a call from
Baron Alwine to come back
to Nottingham
immediately.
Climb aboard, Ms. Cleo,
and we'll take you
to the castle now,
Ah!
Cleo, wait for me!
Who is that?
Forget about him.
Let's go.
Cleo, come back!
Cleo, Cleo, ah!
♪
Could you say that again,
Robin?
Marian, it's important that
I go and talk to Cleo again.
Oh, so is this what you were
trying to tell me about, Robin?
♪
I wanted to show you this,
Marian.
It's a talisman
that Cleo gave to me.
Look.
Hmm.
Marian, it was long ago,
before she was duped by Alwine
and before her decision
to fight me.
Deep down Cleo is good,
I know it.
♪
Well I guess Mr. Kirk will be on
his way somewhere else by now.
I guess.
Think I'll see him again?
You never know,
but you have that stone
to remind you of him.
That's right.
Robin, are you sure?
I know it's risky,
but it's the only way.
She needs someone.
Someone must tell her the truth
about Baron Alwine.
Oh, please don't go, Robin!
It isn't safe!
If you fail you will die,
and I just couldn't bear that!
Please forgive me, Marian, but
I can't leave Cleo all alone,
not now!
(Marian sobbing)
Marian, Marian wait!
Oh, Marian.
Oh, Robin, why must you
always think of others?
Oh, Robin.
♪
Ah, I just wonder what made
Marian change her mind.
♪
Huh?
Ah, what's this?
♪
Will I ever see Robin again?
I understand.
Oh, Marian, thank you.
♪
That sound.
There's only person I know who
makes music like that.
Robin!
Too bad!
Stop whining, Osmond.
She is not the prize.
The real enemy is Robin.
We have to avenge Gilbert!
She is just a means to an end.
Marian.
Die!
Ah, Cleo!
Ah, why can't you understand?
♪
My brother!
You killed my brother
and now I'll kill you!
♪
Ah!
Cleo, look out!
Ahh!
Ah!
Look out!
Knights of the Black Rose,
I command you, let her go!
♪
Now!
Take him!
♪
Marian.
Uh, ah.
Wait!
W--, wait!
That swordplay is familiar.
Ah, ah, but that's impossible.
It cannot be.
It can't be Gilbert.
He's dead.
♪
And anyway,
even if he was alive,
he wouldn't have turned
on his fellow knights.
♪
Uh, ah, ah, Cleo!
Oh, my leg!
Huh?
Oh, it's trapped.
Uh, uh.
I don't want your help, you,
you of all people.
Be quiet!
One more landslide
and we'll both be dead!
♪
It's moving!
He saved me.
I'll get you out of here.
Ah!
Marian,
princess,
how dare those dogs
lay their dirty hands on you?
♪
(sobbing)
Cleo, don't cry.
Ah, we're safe now.
Robin, why did you
have to save me?
You know I was
trying to kill you!
I owe it to Gilbert,
to your brother.
Oh?
Gilbert, he died saving Marian.
Oh.
(owl hooting)
Gilbert!
♪
Marian.
I should've died there.
I wanted to.
I was happy to give
my life for her,
but fate spared me,
and now I know why.
♪
I have to fulfill my destiny
to protect you, Marian.
And for that I need to live.
You may not see me, Marian,
but I swear
that I will protect you
to the end of my days!
Robin, is this really true?
Robin, please wake up.
Robin.
Oh, oh.
\"Dear Robin, being parted
from you is really painful,
but I can bear the pain
because I know you are the only
one who could help Cleo.
You will succeed.
I know it.
Only you could convince her
that Gilbert's death
was not your fault,
but there is another who needs
your kindness and friendship,
Robin.
Promise me you will return.
I will wait for you always.
Your loving friend, Marian.\"
♪
Baron Alwine!
What is it?
The Knights of the Black Rose,
my Lord,
have forced their way
into the castle!
Is Cleo with them?
There is a female, yes, sire.
They demand to see you.
Demand?
They should be
begging on their knees!
They are nothing!
That's enough, Bishop.
But, Baron, they're dangerous!
Yes, I know they are.
I'm not stupid.
Welcome to you all.
It is always a delight
to entertain
the Knights of
the Black Rose
and especially rewarding
to see Cleo here.
Thank you.
My Lord, with your permission,
I have a question to ask you.
Oh, a question.
Well I'd be happy to answer it.
His Lordship is very gracious.
I would be very grateful
if Your Grace would tell me
of the fate of my brother,
Gilbert.
I see.
Tell me, my dear, why do you
need this information?
Have you seen Gilbert's ghost
by any chance?
Gilbert's ghost, my Lord?
Oh no.
But I've seen through
your deception.
Gilbert is alive!
What?
You lied to me, Baron.
You deceived me cruelly.
How...?
I don't know why you deceived
me yet, but I'll find out.
You're an evil liar!
Oh yes, I know I am.
(evil laughter)
Well, well,
I'm an evil liar, eh?
Well that's quite an accusation.
I hope you can prove it,
but only time will tell,
my dear Cleo.
Now, I have no more time to
waste on your childish chivalry.
I'm a busy baron.
You see,
I'm about to become rich
beyond anyone's wildest dreams.
Soon the treasure of the forest
will be mine!
You're evil, evil!
Yes, obviously evil, but don't
forget handsome and rich,
compared to you,
you scum!
What?
You swine!
I'll teach you some manners.
You'll pay for that, Alwine.
Guards!
Whoa!
No!
(evil laughter)
Alwine, you'll pay for this.
♪
Pay for it?
Well at least I can afford it,
which is more than I can say
for you, my dear Cleo.
(evil laughter)
♪
Oh!
Incoming!
They're coming,
they're coming!
The war machine!
This new telescope is amazing,
Bishop.
I can see the enemy
and they're pathetic!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Just imagine life
without Robin Hood,
with tons and tons of treasure.
Hmm.
Their puny defenses will be
flattened under my war machine.
Forward!
♪
Everybody ready?
Come on, Alwine!
I'm ready for them.
We'll show ya, big mouth!
I'll tear ya apart!
Come on!
Think you're big, huh?
We'll pulverize ya!
Go away!
Come get us!
Have that!
Yeah!
And that!
And that too!
I hope this machine works, Much.
Oh.
Of course it does.
I built it.
Ah!
Maybe we should scram.
Yeah.
Maybe you're right.
Retreat!
Run for it!
Much, that cannon was useless!
I'm gonna whoop ya
just as soon as I get ya!
(Baron laughing)
There is no one in England
as horrible as me!
I'm bad and I'm to be king.
(evil laughter)
Ah, it's huge!
Ahh.
Robin!
Robin, come back!
♪
Alwine, I'll get you!
Alwine!
Huh?
Ah, he never gives up.
Mmm.
♪
Time to end your evil, Alwine.
Ah.
♪
Go ahead and shoot, if you dare.
Ah, let go!
Get down!
Oh, ah!
No!
Cleo!
Ah, ah!
Robin!
You shoot and she dies,
Huntington!
Go ahead and shoot.
I'll kill her
no matter what you do!
Robin!
I look for justice, not revenge!
Robin, fire!
(evil laughter)
Robin!
♪
Ohh!
Ahh!
The treasure of the forest!
♪
I knew I was right.
The golden cross itself
is showing the way.
Soon the treasure will be mine!
Fire the incendiary device!
Raze Sherwood Forest
to the ground!
♪
Whoa!
Don't just stand there
you stupid nobleman!
Move yourself!
(explosion)
Ah!
(fire crackling)
♪
Ah!
There's Marian.
Oh!
Hello, Marian.
Oh, oh!
The Baron wants to talk to ya.
Marian!
The fire's outta control.
It's gonna be a disaster!
Robin, we've got
to do somethin'!
You get the others and
start fighting the fire!
I'll try to rescue
Cleo and Marian.
Come back!
Robin, it's too dangerous!
Cleo, Marian, hang on!
I'm coming!
♪
Huh?
Ah, uh, uh!
♪
It's you, Gilbert!
So, Huntington,
is it destiny that makes us
always fight among flames?
I first saw you
in your burning castle.
A lot has changed since then,
eh, Robin?
Gilbert, Cleo and Marian
are prisoners!
Don't you care about them?
Don't you care how you die,
Robin?
Yah!
♪
Do move along.
It won't be long now,
Bishop,
and soon the treasure
will be ours.
Oh yes, lovely, and equal shares
for you and me, eh?
Ah, ha.
Marian!
No you don't!
Ah, ah!
What are you thinking of,
Gilbert?
I'm gonna kill you,
Robin of Huntington.
Don't you realize
you're wasting time?
Marian must be rescued and Cleo,
your own sister.
They can wait a little longer.
Right now I'm gonna kill you!
Huh?
♪
Marian!
Die!
Oh!
Take that, ah!
♪
Gilbert, look out!
Ahh!
No!
Oh, Gilbert.
No one could survive that.
Gilbert.
My bow.
Robin!
Huh?
Robin, what are you doing
wasting time here?
Marian and Cleo
need to be rescued!
Alwine's got them!
Hurry, Chief!
We can't hold on much longer!
The fire's closing in.
We'll take care of things here.
Now get a move on!
Mm-hmm.
Thanks, Little John, old buddy.
Did I hear right?
Hey Chief, what'd he call you?
Um, he called me buddy.
Hmm.
Marian!
♪
Faster!
Yah!
Faster now!
Look!
Hmm!
We must not let this
stop our mission, Baron.
We must press on.
But how are we going to
get through that?
Hmm, forward.
Clear the way.
Hyah, hyah, hyah!
Ah, oh, ha, oh.
The path is clear now,
Baron Alwine.
We can continue.
Good.
Huh?
Baron?
I'm falling, ah!
Oh, do get up, man.
Get off me!
Do you have no respect?
Scum like you deserve
no respect.
Oh do shut up!
Ah, oh!
Wha--?
♪
Come on!
Not so fast!
Ah!
Out of my way!
It's got me!
Be careful, Baron!
Baron, please help me
or the monster will get me!
Well, it's not getting me.
Give him a cake.
Please, my Lord,
don't desert me.
If you don't let go of me,
you fool,
I shall be forced
to free myself with this!
Help him, Baron!
Don't listen to her!
Save yourself!
No!
Get off!
Ahh!
Ah, ah, run!
Marian!
Over here!
(evil laughter)
This'll take the smile off
of your face, Bishop.
No amount of gold
will help you now.
Marian!
Oh, Bishop.
Robin!
♪
Oh no, Robin, you mustn't!
I cannot forgive Alwine.
It may be wrong but I must use
the sacred bow to kill him!
♪
No, Robin, don't!
Sacred bow, give me strength!
No, Robin, it's forbidden!
Eh?
Robin!
Alwine, goodbye!
I'll kill the girl!
You haven't got the guts
and, anyway,
should you fire that bow,
Hartford will kill Cleo
and I will slaughter Marian
in my one final moment!
Kill me, but you will sentence
these girls to perish with me.
Go ahead!
Fire!
Oh, oh.
Mmm.
♪
Oh.
(evil laughter)
Robin!
Why ha, ha, ha.
What a good idea to bring
these girls along.
So, Robin, uh?
♪
Ahh!
Oh, Gilbert!
Gilbert,
I don't believe it!
Ah!
Gilbert, but you&
Come on, Robin.
Ah!
Gilbert!
Yah!
♪
Robin!
Gilbert!
Oh.
I think we should
creep away quietly.
No,
let's run like blazes!
Gilbert, it is madness for you
and I to be fighting like this!
We should be joining forces.
Joining forces with Alwine, yes.
I knew you'd say that.
Gilbert, listen!
My first duty is
to kill Robin Hood.
You know that.
Yah, ahh!
No!
Ah!
Oh no!
He's been injured, Marian!
Robin!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I've been waiting
for this day all my life.
I'm so happy!
Ha, ha, ha, ah.
That's just gold,
you dribbling fool.
The real treasure of the forest
is up there!
Ah, uh, the spear
of eternal life.
That is the greatest prize,
and with it
I will be all powerful,
king of all I desire!
Ah, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I must help
Marian and Cleo!
Are you in pain?
Huh?
(evil laughter)
♪
What's the matter, Robin?
Lost your fighting spirit?
I always thought the Huntingtons
were a courageous family.
It appears that I was wrong.
♪
Ah?
Not so fast!
Gilbert, stop now!
Robin!
♪
If you use your Father's
bow now,
you may find your arm
a little painful.
♪
Must find some strength
from somewhere.
Oh, Marian and Cleo
have to be rescued
and the only way
to do it
is to kill Gilbert!
Goodbye, Robin!
Gilbert, you mustn't!
No, Gilbert!
No!
♪
(evil laughter)
The spear of eternal life,
the real treasure of the forest.
Come to me.
I want you.
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, oh.
♪
Whoa, oh, oh!
Ohh, ahh, oh!
Ohh, oh, oh!
Oh!
Ahh.
(Baron screaming)
(Bishop and Baron screaming)
Incredible!
Help me!
Somebody turn it off!
Please help me!
Help me!
Robin, Gilbert,
please, please help me!
Ah, oh, oh, my arm.
Ah, oh, oh, oh.
Ahh.
Help me, Alwine!
No, it's not fair!
It's not fair!
I mustn't die like this!
I'm going to be King of England!
This is not my destiny!
(coughing)
It's swallowing them up.
♪
They must've perished.
Oh!
Ah!
Cleo!
Robin,
oh!
Gilbert!
Marian!
Ah, hold on!
Ahh!
Uh, ah, ah!
Marian, I'm coming!
Robin!
Marian, what can I do?
Here!
The golden cross!
Marian, you mustn't!
Robin, you must take the cross.
Be brave!
Take it, Robin!
I entrust it to you!
Use it wisely!
The cross is sacred, Robin,
and very powerful!
Don't let me down, Robin!
Cleo!
Oh, Gilbert, I beg your
forgiveness, my brother!
♪
Please, Gilbert!
Ohh, ohh.
Huh?
Ah!
An arrow!
But you are forbidden!
Stop talking nonsense!
I am a knight
of the Black Rose
and I intend to fight my way
outta here!
Hah!
Don't fire!
Hmm, ah, uh.
Uh, uh.
For Cleo!
Ah!
♪
Gilbert, what have you done?
The bow must not be fired by one
with evil in his heart.
It is true.
My heart was once filled
with evil against you, Robin,
and against my own sister,
my own dear Cleo.
♪
Ahh, ahh!
Don't give up!
Ah, uh, ah, ah, ah, ah, Robin.
♪
You can't die!
Huh?
Ah, it's no good, Robin.
It's over.
It seems that destiny
requires me to die here.
No, Gilbert!
Robin, goodbye.
I hope you can forgive me.
Ah, uh, uh.
The forest is angry.
I've always fought Alwine.
We've always had our battles,
but now we are
harming the forest,
and nature is punishing us.
Robin, the golden cross
of Lancaster,
its power's a great mystery.
Robin, use it wisely.
♪
Oh, oh, ah, oh,
the golden cross.
♪
Ah, uh, uh!
Holy Father,
we beg for mercy.
♪
Don't let me down, Robin,
or Cleo,
or Gilbert.
What have we done?
♪
Mother Nature,
please forgive us!
♪
Please!
Forgive us.
Ah!
Don't let me down, Robin!
♪
Look at this forest, friend!
The fire's out!
Sure!
Wow!
Where's the fire?
Huh?
Oh, it's over!
Oh!
Ah!
It's a miracle!
Thank goodness!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
It's a miracle.
It's a miracle!
(laughter)
♪
(snoring)
Mmm?
Oh, where am I?
What?
Did I imagine it?
Could it be
that I was really
up there looking down?
Oh wow!
♪
Gilbert, do you
really have to go?
Mm-hmm.
I never thought
I would say this.
I shall miss you, Robin,
my friend.
We will both miss you, hey,
Marian?
Hmm?
That's right.
Goodbye, Gilbert.
Robin.
Cleo.
I've always liked you, Robin.
Haven't I, Marian?
Mm-hmm.
And I've always liked you,
Gilbert.
Ah, um-umm.
Well, that's the first time
I've seen Gilbert blush.
(laughter)
Farewell.
Show them what it is
they must defend.
They must see the universe
as their mother.
She gave them life.
They must show her love.
♪
♪ Deep in
their forest hideaway ♪
♪ The outlaws have made
their getaway ♪
♪ From the sheriff and his men
♪ Their philosophy on life
is to live and rob again ♪
♪ Then to give it to the poor
♪ Come along if you can
to join our merry band ♪
♪ Robin,
ride on and never lose ♪
♪ Robin, good luck to you
♪ Robin of the forest
♪ God save the king
♪ And God help the poor
♪ If anyone can save us
♪ Of this you can be sure
♪ Robin, ride on
and never lose ♪
♪ Robin, good luck to you
♪ Robin of the forest
♪