Ever since I was little... I've
been having this same dream.
In it, I see this girl.
She's someone I've never met.
But, I'm in love with her.
The kind of deep love you
can only feel after a lifetime.
And she loves me
back, just as much.
But... In the end,
something freaky happens...
The sky takes her back
somehow... and I wake up from
the dream...
unnerved and restless.
Hello, everyone... Well...
I am Eishirou Sugata,
resident genius.
This here is my
assistant, Pretty.
Look here. There appears
to be some type of
anomalous hole
orbiting the earth.
Scientists around the world
have been working together
to try and solve
the mystery of its origin.
They've even dropped monitoring
devices into the anomaly,
but haven't settled
on any logical conclusion...
But you see, their
hypotheses are flawed,
because they are
grounded in reality.
As I'm sure you're
aware, Columbus,
who discovered the Americas,
was able to stand an egg
on its end by simply
thinking outside of the box.
This story illustrates that
no one believes in the unreal
until they see
it for themselves.
It's the nature of people.
It's similar to the world
beneath a girl's skirt.
Something truly a mystery.
But I have the ability to see!
I can see the keywords
that connect everything...
"A Whole New World."
Now, the next issue is what
makes up this "Whole New World?"
Speaking metaphorically,
you could say that
under the girl's skirt.
Tomo, come on!
Would you get up already?!
We're gonna
be late for school!
Just five more minutes.
Argh... For crying
out loud, get up!
Sohara?! What's wrong?!
You know I hear that's a
good sign. When the flag's
full mast first thing
in the morning. Come on.
Nooo!
At least drink some
milk before we head out.
Oh, yeah, thanks.
And your tie's all messed up.
It doesn't matter how old you
get, you still act like a child.
Alright, let's get going.
We live in Sorami City. It's a
small town with a population of
about seven thousand,
completely surrounded
by mountains. It's nice.
The town isn't known
for anything in particular...
If it was, it would be the
smile on the old farmer's face.
Or maybe, the humongous,
four hundred year old cherry
blossom tree that sits on that
hill right outside of town.
Reinforcing this
sense of isolation...
Everyone always complains about
how there's nothing to do here,
but I like it. It's my kind
of place. My motto is this:
Stay awake!
Peace and quiet is
the only way to live.
I like to watch TV, eat,
take a nap during class...
The most perfect thing you
can ask for is just a thread of
peace and quiet running through
your life. Wouldn't you agree?
Save me.
Huh?
The sky has me in its grip.
Tomo? Wake up! Tomoki!
Class is over if
you hadn't noticed.
You had the dream
again, didn't you?
Oh, great. Am I crying?
Look, Tomoki. You've
been having that dream
ever since you were a little
kid. Think maybe you should
see a doctor about
it or something?
It's just some stupid
dream, it's not like
it's ruining my
life or anything!
Okay. Wait, I have an idea.
What if we run it by
Sugata? See what he thinks?
No freakin' way! I don't
wanna get wrapped up with
some dude who just looks
like he attracts trouble.
Hey! Everyone come quick!
Some moron's about
to jump off the roof!
Huh?!
Jump off the roof?
The wind is good today.
Although I'm not exactly happy
with the direction
it's blowing.
But it won't be a
problem for takeoff!
Don't do it! You're
insane! You'll die!
Oh! Hello there, Miss
President. Good morning.
Um, is someone
gonna jump off the roof?
Take a look.
Wha--?! Sugata?!
Shouldn't you be
trying to stop him?
I could ask him to come
down, but he won't listen.
I'll worry about
it after he falls.
Could you be
more irresponsible?
I mean, you're
student council president,
you gotta do something!
If you're talking about
insurance, I already bought
a whole lot of it.
Several million worth of
life insurance to be exact.
Wow, that's a lot.
Don't you stand there actin'
all impressed! Come on, Prez.
Aren't you two, like,
childhood friends or something?
Shouldn't you show the
tiniest bit of consideration?
Are you suggesting
I'm not worried
about him in the slightest?
No, that's not... uh...
Are you suggesting I believe
it might not be such a bad thing
to watch my dear friend plummet
to his death with a big smile
spread across my face
as the cherry blossoms
bloom in the background?
I didn't say that.
And are you suggesting I'm
even considering the remote
possibility that after I've
made my claim on the insurance,
I'll travel the world on
the finest luxury cruise liner
while I mourn my
friend's untimely passing?
Um, are you?
What do you think? Are you
sure you want that answer?
Uh, no.
He jumped.
Be careful!
So... You wanna head back?
Hang on Tomo,
what about your dream?
I am so not
talking to that guy!
What are you talking about?
Tomo's just being stupid.
He wants to ask Sugata
some questions. We
heard he's in the know
regarding "out there"
kinds of things.
You'd be right about that. He's
creepy, perverted beyond belief,
weird beyond comprehension,
and without a doubt,
the freakiest four-eyed
guy I know of.
But he's dependable
for what you need.
Dependably nuts!
Well, who the Hell
else are we gonna ask?
I mean, you refuse to
go see a professional...
I just wanna live
in peace and quiet!
Fine then. Have it
your way... Jackass.
I understand every
word of your concerns.
Many intelligent people
believe dreams to be
electrical signals your brain
sends out when
processing memories. In
other words, your desires or
your memories become your
dreams during your sleep.
O-kay...
But that's nothing more than a
hypothesis grounded in reality.
And you can't explain
the unreal using real terms.
Look at this.
No, not that!
You know what that is?
The black spot? No.
Of course you don't.
What?
Because you've already
concluded you don't know.
There are scientists who have
spent years researching this
and have yet to figure out
the slightest thing about it.
But I understand it. I know
exactly what the true nature is
behind this hole...
and of course...
I also know what
your dream means.
Both of them are part
of A Whole New World!
Such fools in the
scientific community!
Something with this much
mass, this much displacement!
It can't be anything but a whole
new world floating up there!
This recurring dream you've
been having is also connected to
this whole new world.
Have faith in me and I will
unlock the mystery
of this dream of yours!
That's great.
Sohara...
At precisely midnight tonight,
this Whole New World of which
I speak will
fly over this town.
Do you mind if
I come check it out?
Sounds just fine.
This is bad. I can
already hear it. The sound of
my beautiful peace and quiet
being torn apart at the seams!
We'll meet at the old
cherry blossom tree next to
the shrine at midnight. We're
going to see this together.
I'm sorry. But my mother
told me I can't stay out
past midnight tonight.
Apologies, Mikako
needs me tonight...
It doesn't look like
I'll be able to join you.
To everyone who said they'd
come up here with me, tonight,
thanks a lot. I'm looking
around and guess what?
No one. Sincerely, Tomoki.
To Hell with this!
I'm outta here!
Oh, it's Sugata.
'Ey, what's up, weirdo?
Get the Hell outta there!
I just did another pass
over the most recent data
and something odd is going on.
I'm heading over there now.
What? You're breaking
up. I can't hear.
The hole is moving...
What?
You're in danger...
What the--?!
Oh, no... It's a person!
No. It's not a person.
A person doesn't have...
A person doesn't... have wings!
Don't think about
how weird this is.
The whole mess
just stinks of trouble.
Run away!
What the Hell is happening?!
She'll be
fine. I'm sure of it.
The chick fell
outta the freakin' sky
without a scratch on her.
I'm not getting
involved. No way.
"Peace and quiet is the best."
That's my motto
and I'm sticking to it.
That's it. That's what I say.
Those are the words I live by.
Ah! Damn it!
Ah, man! All I want,
is to live in peace!
After this I'm gonna go home,
watch TV, and pass the Hell out.
Begin imprinting process.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am a Pet-Class Angeloid.
My purpose is to fulfill
your every want and desire.
You are my master.
Hey, Tomo! I'm
on cleaning duty today,
so I'm gonna
head off to school!
Get your ass out of
bed so you're not late.
Good morning... Master.
Oh right, I forgot
about the winged chick who
fell from the sky yesterday.
Master, please make a command.
Give me any order that will
please you. Anything you desire.
Angeloids were created
for the sole purpose of
bringing our masters
pleasure. It is all we know.
So whatever I want, eh?
Yes.
Your...
My what?
Well, how about
a bunch of cash?
You are requesting
a sum of money?
That was almost weird. I was
about to get my freak on with
an alien creature
from space or wherever.
What's wrong with my head?
Yeah, duh. If I had
that much money I could buy
anything I wanted
in the whole world.
Initiating transport.
You're screwing with my head!
What is that card thingy?
Lemme see it! Hand it over!
In your language,
this card would be known as
a teleportation device.
Teleportation?
I hear your request,
and all I need to do is
order the required
materials from the Synapse.
What's the Synapse?
I have no stored information
regarding the Synapse.
Those databanks are clear. After
all, I have only just awoken,
so I am void of much data.
I am a Pet-Class Angeloid.
My type is Alpha. Ikaros.
I was manufactured by
the Synapse... for you.
For your sole pleasure.
I don't care about all
that noise. Too confusing.
What I wanna know
is what else can you do?
Anything.
Anything?!
Correct.
Come on! Aw...
These stupid things have
grown again haven't they?
There's no point
in them being this big.
Oh, yeah! Being
invisible kicks ass!
Master, why are we here?
Living a man's dream, Ikaros.
That's what we're doing.
Something about men, everything
comes down to our libidos.
Oh, and food.
Now, let's mess with her some.
That was awesome! I can't
believe I actually got her!
Master... Please explain.
That, my good
Ikaros, was punishment.
Punishment for the
vicious girl who's always
karate-chopping me
with her stupid hands!
It was punishment?
Okay, Ikaros,
time for the next one!
Transport!
Time... stop!
Master?
Yes! Everywhere
I wanna go is mine!
The world is
mine for the taking!
Let's keep moving!
I know. But that's what I
told the loser. Yeah, right?
I am King of the World!
Your panties are mine!
How is your dinner, Master?
It's lightin' up my tastebuds.
But what is this stuff, anyway?
I've never had it before.
The card summoned a
quantum food changer which
transformed the air
in such a way as to--
Forget about it.
That crap's way over my head.
Do you have any
further commands, Master?
Not right now. Uh...
'Cept maybe... you stripping?
All right.
No, no! Reel that in,
seriously! I was just kidding!
It was a joke!
Cancel that order!
I cannot cancel
orders. I was not given
capacity for that function.
Do you have any
further orders for me?
No! No! Nothing I can think
of! In fact, I'm exhausted!
We're done for today! We can
just pick up the whole thing
where we left off
tomorrow! Whattya say?
That said... I'm
happy I've gotten to do
everything I wanted to.
I guess the only thing left
on my list is to
take over the world!
Tomo, time to wake up!
Why weren't you at
school yesterday, dumbass?
The teacher was pissed! You're
in so much trouble today!
Open up the freakin' door.
I heard you. Ease up.
What do you... want? Hey,
uh... Sohara? What the heck?
World Domination will be
complete momentarily, Master.
Wha-huh?
I activated a World Domination
Program while you slept.
Don't tell me...
According to my research, not
a single human on Planet Earth
would recognize you
as their supreme ruler.
It therefore seems the program
determined the best course of
action was to
erase all other humans
on the planet from existence.
Wait... every other human
being... on the planet?
Correct.
Can you cancel that?
I cannot. I was not given
capacity for that function.
I can't believe this.
I only wanted a normal life.
A peaceful one. And look at
what I get. The exact opposite.
Is there really no one
left on the entire planet?
I apologize, Master.
I interpreted your
statement as an order.
What do you wish now?
Would it remedy the situation
if I destroy myself?
Yeah, I guess that'd
make things a little better.
I've had enough of this BS.
Yes, Master.
Master?
I was just kidding.
It's just a joke, you know?
Go ahead and cancel
that last order, okay?
I cannot cancel an order.
Why the hell not?! You haven't
done a single thing wrong!
You've just been following every
stupid order I've spit out.
Come on, there's no
reason for you to die!
I was not given
capacity for that function.
I'm begging you!
You have to help me.
Everyone left because of me.
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
Don't leave me here all alone.
I'm on my knees.
Cancel that order.
Stay... Stay with me, please!
I will, Master.
I wish this whole mess was
nothing but one bad nightmare.
Keep your angel. Treasure her.
Huh?
And never part
with her. Not ever.
Hey, Tomo! I'm on cleaning
duty today, so I'm gonna
head off to school! Get your ass
out of bed so you're not late.
Was that some kinda
tripped out dream or what?
I feel all dizzy.
Whoa, man. I can't even tell
which way is up.
What's my problem?
Are you well
this morning, Master?
You!
You wished everything was
nothing more than a nightmare
so I activated a program
that made it all into a dream
and returned
the world to normal.
You can actually do that?
Did I do bad?
Hell no! You did a great
thing! You're the best ever!
But to be honest... I'm
more tired than I've ever been.
Pardon me, Master.
Is this something you want
to stay as part
of your dream as well?
Huh? Is what something?
You told me stay
with you, then you said
you wanted
everything to change back.
Would it be better...
if I remained a part of
your dream state?
I think you should do
whatever you want, Ikaros.
Master? I do not understand.
Do I have to
explain everything?!
No, Master.
I say this all the time, but the
only thing I want in this world
is to live a normal, peaceful
life. 'Cept there's this chick
with a vicious karate chop
who's always out to get me.
And some freakboy who thinks
he can fly, stressing me out.
And last, but certainly
not least, I got Ikaros.
The girl who
fell from the sky.
And that's how
this whole thing began.
These are days I don't
think I'll ever forget.
Y-You don't have to stand
so close to me, you know.
Jeez! Close the door!
Next time... "An Airborne,
Prismatic, Panty Adventure."