Just where do you think
you're running off to, Beta?
What was that?
Ikaros. What's the matter?
Nothing.
Gamma!
You got it. We're the
Angeloid Interceptors,
type Gamma and type Harpy.
It's the Uranus
Queen's swan song.
We're here to
take the bitch down.
Don't you
worry about a thing.
You see, Master
asked us to do this.
I'll bet you didn't know
he's been watching over you
this entire time. Actually, he's
been quite worried about you.
He's worried about me?
Well, he did tell you to take
on the Uranus Queen by yourself.
And that's a Hell of
a tall order for anyone,
even one of us.
When he realized you
might get hurt attempting it,
he acted quickly to mount
a rescue. He sent us here to
bring you home
as soon as possible.
Sounds like Master's
pretty lonely without you
up there with him, Beta.
Master's worried about me.
And he's actually lonely
without me too?
I never expected that.
As much as she enjoys
hanging around those insects,
this must be torturing her.
She'll destroy the Uranus
Queen, kill the humans,
and then return to me filled
with joy, certain I'm going to
applaud what a good job
she did. And that's the moment
I'll tell the wretched thing,
"It's time to send
your ass to the scrapyard."
I can't wait to see the
horrified face she makes
when I drop
that bomb on her.
There is no more time.
Hear me. You must
save the angel, please.
She is being held by the sky.
That same
weird-ass dream again.
Are you finally
waking up, Master?
Yeah. Where's Nymph?
Well, she's...
What?! Are you serious?
Nymph pulled another
disappearing act?!
Correct. This is becoming
something of a pattern.
She's makin' me
crazy! What's her deal?
Like Ikaros said,
she's always takin' off.
Come on, you have to
have some idea why, Tomoki.
Did you do
something bad to her?
It wouldn't be the first
time you did something dumb.
What are you--?!
Whoa! No! I didn't do anything
wrong, okay? We're cool.
You sure? Cuz the
look on your face says
the exact opposite of the
words coming out of your mouth.
Stop reading into it, it's
nothing! Leave me alone!
Come to think of it,
I did see Nymph flying toward
the forest last night. At the
time it didn't seem that odd.
You mean it?
But now that I think
back, she might have been
fretting over something.
Or I could be wrong.
Well, maybe we should
go out and look for her.
Don't you think? She can't miss
our Christmas party tonight!
I'm not worried about it,
she came back last time
she did this. Let's just
focus on setting up the party.
We'll wait for
her if we have to.
Then how about we go
find a tree for this shindig.
It's one of the big things we're
missing. And speaking of big,
I have to say I am
partial to the large ones.
You got any idea where
we can find a big one?
I actually know of an
excellent spot to look.
There's an ideal tree near
the riverbed next to my place.
That's great. But do you have
something to chop it down with?
I'm just saying if you don't,
you could always borrow my axe.
No problem there. I have the
perfect axe for chopping wood.
I'll leave the
rest o' this to you.
See you in a little bit.
That's amazing! You're fast!
No, wait! Stop! Ikaros,
you're whipping too fast now!
You have to stop it!
All right.
Aw, man. You charred the bowl.
I have failed.
Ah, no worries! We're
still having fun, right?
Just us girls,
making a cake together,
finally having
some bonding time.
I just wish Nymph could be
here to enjoy it all with us.
What is that?
Oh, yeah. I brought it
thinking we could use some of
these pictures to
decorate for the party.
Brings back some fun memories,
huh? We've done so much
in the short amount of
time we've known each other.
Heh. Yeah, but this one
right here is my favorite
of the bunch. When we first
met, I never imagined you and I
would hit it off
as well as we have.
But I'm glad we did.
Perfect. Seems the information
you gave us was accurate.
This is an excellent location.
No place for her to hide.
And we've got a
great vantage point.
We shall be
proceeding as planned.
Starting from here on out, we're
going to need you to hide us
with your P-Stealth system.
That's our best angle of attack.
Don't worry. When you
need help, we'll back you up.
Back me up?
That's right. With
our super-hot compressed
projectile cannon, Prometheus.
It fires vaporized matter
heated to three
thousand degrees Celsius
at four kilometers a second.
If she doesn't have the time to
deploy Aegis, the Uranus Queen
will be no different
than any of us in a battle.
We'll get her in one shot.
Hold on! I thought the orders
Master gave were for the two
of you to bring her back
in one piece, not destroy her!
In fact, I thought you were
supposed to talk
her into returning!
Well, that's true. But we do
have to protect ourselves if
things don't go
according to plan.
Still gotta cover
our asses, don't we?
We need you to do everything
you can to keep us from
having to use
these dangerous toys.
It'll be fine. I'm
sure you'll be able to do
a great job convincing her.
This is just insurance.
All that we do here is for
our master. If you succeed,
he will have great cause
to rejoice. Don't you think?
Master... will be
happy with me then.
I understand.
But promise me
you won't interfere
until I finish
trying to persuade her.
Oh, sure.
Of course we won't.
I can't help but wonder what
your true Master would think
if he learned what
you were doing here.
Little Miss Weapon of Death!
What... are you doing?
Look, Nymph. The
sky here is so vast.
It's true. Angeloids
aren't designed to smile.
Not unless we have humans
around to help us learn.
This cage... is
like our chokers.
If that's true...
they want out.
Hey, where ya going?
I just... need to...
go get something I forgot.
Why don't you just
give Tomoki a call?
He's already out picking
up things for the party.
Oh, no. I'll just...
Ikaros, remember you promised
you wouldn't lie anymore.
You don't have to. You're
surrounded by your friends here.
You can talk to
us about anything.
You know that, don't you?
Anyway... The cake'll
be out of the oven soon,
so... hurry back.
Ikaros. Whatcha doin'?
Did you come down here
to pick me up?
Awesome. Perfect timing.
You can help me
carry one of these bags.
I got a whole bunch of
stuff. Party poppers. Tinsel.
Way more than we need.
Master...
Oh wait, you're gonna
freak. Check this out.
Isn't this hilarious?
Stupid creepy Santa mask.
Master...
C'mon, you gotta try
it on. Just for a sec.
That looks kick ass!
Goodbye.
Huh?
I've come to
tell you goodbye.
I know our time together
was short. And I apologize
for all the trouble
I've caused you.
But, Master, I will never
forget you. I promise...
These memories... I'm
going to keep them forever.
Wait. What the Hell? Is this
your attempt at making a joke?
Look Ikaros...
I love you, Master.
And I always have.
Goodbye.
That had to have been
caused by some kind of
attack from the sky.
Beginning data scan
of the impact crater.
Analysis indicates
Interceptor-Class Angeloids,
type Gamma and type Harpy.
That's Nymph's signal.
But most likely, I am
their target. I will have to
fight them as the weapon
Master hates so much.
I can't go back to him anymore.
I won't ever see him again.
"Goodbye?!" That's crap!
Wow, it's huge!
We couldn't find the perfect
tree so we settled on this one.
Mikako's heart
was set on a big tree,
so that's
precisely what we got.
Is Ikaros here?! Guys?!
Tomo?
Dammit!
Wait! Tomo, where
are you going?!
First Ikaros and Nymph
show up out of nowhere
and then they just vanish.
Did they even consider the fact
that I might be
worried about them?
That's why I didn't
want to live with them,
cuz I knew I'd get attached.
If they're gone, I
guess at least I'd get
my peace and quiet back.
I mean, that's all I
ever really wanted, right?!
Hi, Nymph.
As I expected, the second I
disabled my stealth functions,
you found me.
I'm sorry, Alpha.
But I had to get you
alone for a minute to talk.
I've kept quiet about
it since I showed up,
but the real
reason I'm here
is to take you
back to the sky.
Of course.
Okay then. So you've known?
Why am I even looking for them?
Sorry to keep
you waiting. Tomoki.
Sugata, why are you here?
You're looking for
Ikaros and Nymph aren't you?
According to the eyewitness
reports I've gathered from
the area she shouldn't
have gone too far from here.
Judging by her direction,
air speed, and abilities,
I think it'd be best if we
were to search this area here.
But if so...
I know exactly what's going
through that brain of yours.
Hop on, I'll give you a pump.
That's not exactly fair.
You're running off to do
all the cool stuff without me.
Why?
I said why?!
What are you doing?
You said you'd let
me try to convince her!
Why did you just attack
her out of nowhere?!
Ha. You're such
an idiot. We lied.
Idiot or not, she helped us
do this without much effort.
Good point. Guess we
should say thanks, Nymph.
We've got a lot on our plate,
appreciate the shortcut.
What are you talking
about? What about Master?
We're here for one
thing. We need to collect
her Uranus system
core. The variable wings.
Master asked us to bring
that back and only that.
Thanks for taking time
to play with us, Nymph.
But you told me--
And now we're finished
with you. Get lost.
Please. Don't do this.
Yeah. This was
just way too easy.
Bye-bye, Uranus Queen.
Stop it! Tomoki would
never get over this!
Paradise Song!
Mikako?
Yeah, what are
you doing here, Prez?
You're in a hurry,
and I can help. See?
Tomoki wait.
No, I want you to stay here.
Not gonna happen!
I'm going with you!
You can't! We're
gonna go to the--
Ikaros and Nymph
are my friends too!
It doesn't matter
if you like it or not!
If you don't take me with
you, I'll karate chop you!
And I won't stop
'til you're dead!
Sohara.
You got ruined!
You're in pieces!
Nymph...
Hey. What's with the banner?
They were Sohara's idea.
Let's see. "Happy
Birthday, Ikaros and Nymph."
Do Angeloids
even have birthdays?
I dunno. I asked them
and they said they didn't.
So I talked about it
with Sugata and Prez,
and we decided
to give them one.
I suppose it makes
sense for Christmas
to be the birthday for angels.
Why're you doing all this?
Well, Ikaros is still so...
I dunno, she's like a
porcelain doll or something.
Never smiling or anything.
And Nymph's tries to hide it,
but it's obvious
she feels lonely.
So we decided to take today's
Christmas party and make it
their birthday party too.
Thought it might cheer them up.
Oh, and Tomoki,
look at this... Ta-da!
A photo album I made with all
the stuff we've done together!
Wow, this takes me back. It's
from our camping trip, right?
And this one's from our day
at the beach. I look great.
There's pictures from
the cultural festival, too.
Here, look.
These are really nice shots.
And I'm sure Ikaros and Nymph
will smile without
even thinking about it
when they set
their eyes on these.
I hope so. I had no idea what to
get for them, so I thought this
would at least
be a nice gesture.
What's wrong, Tomoki? You don't
look too keen about all this.
You do want to do something
nice for them, right?
Something to give them
a reason to truly smile.
I don't think I can.
All I was ever good at
was makin' them cry.
I've sure never made either
one of them smile before.
You're like Sohara.
Huh?
Even if you can't help, there
must be something you can do.
Something only you
can do. That is if you
don't want to
regret everything forever.
I wonder what kind of
presents they would like.
There's gotta be
something I could buy that
would make them happy.
No way. You took a direct
hit from the Prometheus.
How are you even standing?!
I sure don't know.
Why don't you try asking
the two of them directly?
Yeah, I think that's
what I'm going to do.
But first we
gotta bring 'em home.
This... This is terrible.
Nymph's wings,
they were beautiful.
What happened here?!
Variable wing system:
safeties removed.
Alpha Stop! Tomoki
will find out, you can't!
Activate Mode:
Uranus Queen. Now.
Alpha!
Master, I'm so sorry.
I have been lying to you
from the beginning.
I am a strategic Battle Class
Angeloid, type Alpha, Ikaros.
I am the weapon
you hate so very much.
Yeah, I know.
Ikaros, listen. When I
told you I didn't want you to
be a weapon, it's
because I felt bad for you.
What?
You "adopted" a watermelon and
started raising baby chicks.
You have such a kind heart.
The idea that you were created
to be a killing machine,
it was just too much.
I didn't want that for you.
Thank you.
But you know, I'll tell you how
I'm looking at it right now.
Right now I am more
than happy you're a weapon.
Because now you
can save our friend.
Yes, my Master.
Ikaros. You have to
save Nymph. Kick their ass!
I am Type Alpha... Ikaros.
You can do it!
Engage targets!
Damn it! She's coming!
Split up!
Right!
C'mon, let's use this
chance to break Nymph's chain.
Nymph, are you okay?
She's doesn't look good.
Oh, screw this!
I'm sure she has some
loser for a master anyway.
No! You don't know
what might happen!
You bitch!
Die!
Now hold still!
Aegis!
Just fight through it.
Connect.
No, that's--!
The Uranus... System.
Cerceis.
Dammit! You can't cut it
like that, my choker's a bomb.
Once the time limit is up,
they'll send an
ignition code to blow it up.
If you cut off the chain
before then, it might explode.
...been twisted
with this axe handle.
Yeah! Let's try it!
Would you people listen
to what I'm saying?!
Everyone in this entire
area could be killed!
It could blow us
all into oblivion!
Yeah, so, what about it?
If you hadn't figured it out
yet, we're your friends, Nymph.
And when friends are
in trouble, you help them.
We're just doing
what comes naturally.
Why? Alpha. I don't
understand any of this.
We Angeloids have never
thought about happiness since
our inception. This is
just how we were created.
We exist for the sole purpose
of making our masters happy.
But now, all of these
feelings I've been having...
They're so new.
I'm not sure... But I think...
I might feel happy right now.
Perhaps this is true
happiness I'm experiencing.
Alpha? Am I right? Is this it?
Because for the first
time I'm really smiling.
Full retreat of enemy
combatants: Confirmed.
Disengage Uranus Queen Mode.
Yo, Ikaros! Check it out!
Yeah!
I'm so glad.
It's gonna be
a white Christmas.
It's beautiful. I see now.
The sky from down
here, it is like Heaven.
Merry Christmas! And happy
birthday Ikaros and Nymph!
All right, you two,
I got something to say.
I want you to stay here for
as long as you like. So, yeah.
Think of it as my
birthday-slash-Christmas
present to you both. And here.
A little something extra!
Tomo! You're always
pulling this cheap-ass crap.
Just like you did with me.
Well whaddaya know.
Nice job, Alpha.
Holy crap! You just laughed
a little bit, didn't you?!
Huh?
Do it again! Try
doing it one more time!
Laughing.
You dingbat!