The weather looks great today.
Man, I love peace and quiet.
What the Hell?!
Why hello, everyone.
My name is Eishirou Sugata.
And this here is my
assistant, Pretty the Second.
Beginning around the
year of twelve eighty...
and continuing
for many decades,
the world saw a
drastic surge in trade.
The invention of the magnetic
compass made this possible.
However, before the
compass was widely in use,
mariners depended upon
migrating birds and fish
to determine
ideal sailing routes.
Explorers tracked these animals
to discover the New World.
There is an immeasurable level
of potential in the magnetic
compasses of animals.
Go on, Pretty!
Use that internal compass of
yours to show me the New World!
Perhaps I would've
been better off
just cooking her
for dinner instead.
Damn! Why am I
buried in panties again?
I do not know. Perhaps they're
similar to migratory birds.
Oh, come on.
Wait a minute...
Are you tellin' me all the
panties from before came back?
Yes. In fact, I believe
they circumnavigated
the entire globe already.
Wha--?! No way!
It's possible they just
wanted to see you, Master,
so they came back to visit.
Crazy. You came all the
way back here just to see me?
You guys!
Tomo, I am gonna...
Oh god! I better
start runnin'...
Kill! You!
What are all my
panties doing here?!
Why are they in your room?
You're such a
pervert, Tomo! A pervert!
It's so... It's so
horrible! Look, Sohara!
Look at all
this lifeless fabric!
They could've had bright futures
ahead of them, but no...
you had to ruin it!
That's not it, Master.
The effect of the card has
simply worn off again.
Anyway! Every single one of
'em better go in the trash!
I'm starting to get sick
and tired of this foolishness.
Sure! You got it!
Tomoki. If I leave it to you
you'll end up
sniffing every last pair!
I know! Hey, Ikaros...
Yes, Miss, it's right there.
Score!
What? They came back?
Yeah. When I woke up this
morning, the whole flock
of panties came
flying into my room.
That's very interesting.
You know the New World was
discovered by
tracking migratory birds.
If we call the trajectory...
Did I hear right? Something
about having a huge mound
of panties lying around
your house right now?
Uh, yeah.
Let me see if I've got these
sordid details straight.
An innocent teenager has
both used and unused panties
flying around his bedroom like
it's some perverse wonderland?
Well, they're
not flying anymore!
What about the
pair Sohara was wearing?
Are they included in
there as well, Tomoki?
Well, you are a guy, so I guess
I shouldn't act surprised...
That's all I got. No
more questions from me.
Tomo. Damn it, you better
promise you'll throw them out
as soon as you get back home!
Right! I'm on it!
I don't think I can
ever trust him again!
Hey, Tomoki! Have you gotten
rid of those panties yet?
Hello? Tomo? Are
you even listening?
Yeah... Taken care of!
Good. Thank you.
As if I'd ever throw 'em out!
I'm a growing,
maturing teenager!
I have needs! I'd be
a fool to part ways with
such a treasure-trove. It's like
my own personal holy grail!
What the Hell was that?!
Oh lovely. You liar. You
didn't get rid of any of 'em.
Sohara!
Ikaros here was kind enough
to give me a special card
of my own.
She's on my side now.
The panties
will now... explode.
Huh?!
Let me break it down
for ya. If you so much as
look at a pair of panties,
they'll blow up in your face.
Is that what just happened?!
Exactly. I was hoping
it'd make you less of a
perverted freak show.
Don't worry, it only affects
panties within your vicinity,
and it's just for one day.
Judging by the
size of that explosion,
I bet you didn't throw out a
single pair, you big fat liar.
Ikaros and I are gonna treat
ourselves to a girl's day out.
So even though I won't
be here to witness it,
have fun movin'
around the house! Bye!
Sohara, wait!
Feeling some regret?
No. It's just there's um...
A really big bug
crawling on your wall.
No way! Where? Where is it?
Tomoki! C'mon, help
me out, where is it?
Dumbass. You thought I wouldn't
be able to see your panties
under the windowsill,
but you always get dressed
with your window open.
All of that peeping paid off!
You jerk! You're such
a perv. I hate you!
I hope you burn alive today!
'Kay... Let's get
a move on, Ikaros.
One moment... Master is not...
Don't worry about him.
He's on his own today.
I gotta be careful.
If I see any panties today
they'll turn into bombs and
blow my ass to smithereens!
Damn you, Sohara! I'm becoming
a man, so of course I wanna
fondle 'em and
smell 'em and wear 'em!
Anyway, I gotta find
a way outta here, ASAP.
I forgot. I hung all
of them up yesterday.
This is bad. I'm gonna
die if this keeps up!
I gotta find a way
outta here, and fast! Wait...
If I don't look at them,
they can't explode, right?
Oh man, this'll be
easier than I thought.
I mean, this is my own house, so
I just gotta feel my way around.
Okay, down the stairs.
Get to the ground floor...
Oh, that's crap! I can't touch
them either?! Hell with it!
I'll just jump
out of the window!
Aw, lame! I hung 'em
all over the yard yesterday
'cause I was feeling
all Christmassy!
Fine then. Guess I'll
retreat to the bathroom
and catch my breath.
Aw... Son of a--
Something wrong?
I have the feeling
Master is in danger.
So?! Screw that guy,
he needs to be taught
a long overdue lesson.
No way! Those are adorable!
Oh, look! They have
angel wings on them!
I bet they'd
look perfect on you!
Wait a second... I bet
you're still wearing that same
cheap-ass pair of panties
Tomoki bought for you
at the convenience
store, right?
Look, I'm sorry, girl,
that's not gonna fly.
You can't depend on
that perverted mind of his.
Good thing I'm here to help.
I'll pick out some cute
ones for ya! Think of them as
a present from me to you,
to thank you for the card.
It's cute and it fits great!
So tell me a
little about yourself.
Is this the first time you've
ever been someplace like this?
What do you do for fun?
Have you ever been shopping
with your friends before?
With my friends?
I don't... have friends.
Oh, I see...
Ikaros... I... I, um...
I'm sorry for asking
such weird questions...
I remember when
I first moved here...
I felt totally
alone in the world...
So I really do
understand how you must feel.
Back then... my body
was really weak and...
I had to stay indoors
all the time... So, uh...
Tomoki, who lived next
door, we became close friends.
We were always
there for each other.
Sure, he'd bring me worms
and raid my family's fridge,
just like any typical boy.
Sounds like him, right?
But I remember one
birthday, he was real sweet.
Something wrong, sweetheart?
What are you
standing out here for?
I thought when it was
your birthday... a bunch of
your friends were supposed
to come over to your house
for a party and
have cake and ice cream.
Today's my birthday but
no one came to my party.
I'm all alone.
Oh hey.
Tomoki.
This is... real good!
Hold on... That looks familiar.
Is that the birthday cake
my mom bought for me?
Happy birthday. And look,
Sohara! I got a present for ya.
My grandpa gave
it to me yesterday.
It's an orange tree seed.
If you plant it, your
family will be able to
eat oranges every year!
Cool, huh? Do you like it?
Yeah.
Sure brings back memories. He
may act like an immature brat,
but he's one of the
few who understands...
just how other people
feel. He's nice like that.
It may come as a surprise,
but you can really count on him
when it truly matters.
But don't get me wrong.
Ninety-nine percent of
the time he's just a creep.
He prob'ly won't say
anything to you about it...
but I'm pretty sure
he cares about you, too.
And you know,
you do have friends.
Just know you're
not alone, Ikaros. Okay?
Master is in serious danger.
All right. I'm starting
to get worried myself.
Let's head back to the house.
Screw it! Make a run for the
door and hope for the best!
Just a little further!
Almost there!
No... Oh god, no!
No!
What... happened?
Are you okay?
Pull yourself together, Tomoki.
What are you... doing here?
Ikaros informed us of
what happened. We came to
check up on the status
of the panty situation.
I never would
have expected this.
Looks like you've
been through Hell.
I guess... I finally
made it out of the house...
Hell! Yeah!
Hang on... Where's Sohara?
She's inside of the house.
It looks as though the
explosion caused her...
to be thrown
back into the house.
That's crazy!
It's all my fault. None of
this would've happened if
I hadn't landed face
first in her crotch.
You know what to do,
Tomoki. You're the only one
capable of saving Sohara from
the danger that awaits her.
Ma'am...
Take this.
Whoa! What the...?
It's one of those times...
when a man stands up and fights.
Now get in there
and bring an end to
this deviant funhouse
you've created.
That is, of course, if you're
man enough for the job.
Oh, I am on this.
Sergeant Tomoki.
Ready for battle!
Wait for me, Sohara!
Master.
Now you do realize you could
send anyone other than Tomoki
in there and the
panties would never explode.
Oh yes, Sugata, I'm
well aware of that fact.
But you have to admit,
it's a lot more fun
doing it this way, isn't it?
You're still as awful
as you've ever been.
Sohara! Where
are you?! Sohara!
Don't you dare come near me!
Why are you running away?!
My underwear
exploded thanks to you!
I've gone freakin'
commando and it's your fault!
What was that?! Speak up!
I just want this to end!
Wait, Sohara!
Stay where you are!
Oh crap! Not my room!
Sohara! Whatever you do,
don't open the closet!
All my, uh, research
material is... oh.
Wow, there's... So much.
Quick! Take cover! I set
up a booby-trap in here to
protect my treasure
from outsiders!
The light!
What is that?
Duh, it's the booby trap I
was trying to warn you about!
I was up all last
night building it!
The Hyper-Fusion Panty Robot!
Sohara!
Let me go!
I have no choice. The
only way to save Sohara
is to fight the panty
robot! But if anymore panties
explode right now, Sohara
will be in deep trouble!
What should I do?!
Sonny! Sonny boy!
That voice... Grampa!
What's the matter,
Grampa? You look hurt.
Ran into some trouble
with the old lady,
if you know what I mean...
Grampa!
Listen up, now boy, and never
forget what your grandpa's
about to tell ya.
As a man, like me...
Someday down the road you'll
find something you like so much
you won't be
able to give it up.
Odds are it'll come back
to haunt you in the end.
What will you do
when that happens?
Will you turn tail and
run? Of course you won't.
Thank you, Grandpa. As always,
you've helped show me the light.
Tomoki! Save me!
Tomoki!
That's it, sonny boy! Grab
whatcha love and hold onto it!
I believe in you!
Ha-ha!
Show 'em, boy! Show
'em what you're made of!
Panties! Come to me!
Yesss...
Are they dead?
I'd say it's a
definite possibility.
It is Master.
The battle is won...
But not the war.
You're awake.
Oh, hey there.
Thank you, Tomo.
You saved my life, didn't you?
Listen... Today was all
my fault... I'm sorry...
Tomo, you sick bastard!
Pantzer Break! Okay, now
listen up! Your job is to
protect my collection
of booby-mags at all cost!
You are not to let anyone
find 'em, you got me?
Well, time to hit the sack.
Had I known
this would happen,
I never would have
sent an angel to you.
I'm sorry. It looks like
even you will get up caught
in this mess.
She's been spotted.
Next time... "Hot
Night with the Big Fish."