Hello, everyone.
You know me. My name
is Eishirou Sugata.
I'm currently seeking
a new assistant.
In the Age of Discovery,
Ferdinand Magellan found
something significant.
The southern route to
circumnavigate the globe.
It was his crowning achievement
that using his contemporary
ships' logs, he was able to
prove that the earth
was, in fact, round.
This caused a ripple of panic
to course through the network of
cartographers of the time. After
all, it completely destroyed
their concept of the
known world. And their maps.
I believe this type of discovery
could happen again now.
If we could just somehow
seek out this New World.
On a side note, Magellan's log
also made note of "footprints
of giants" near Patagonia.
The possibility exists that
whatever he saw,
still lives on an island
somewhere to this very day.
What about you? Would you
like to be my new assistant?
We're almost to
summer vacation, Ikaros.
And it's getting way
hot. I think maybe we're
gonna have to buy
an air conditioner.
Master, in looking around
us, I think we need to
sort out our
living conditions first.
You might have a point.
The entire house went "boom"
thanks to all those
damn exploding panties.
Hey, I got it! Why
don't we just go stay at
Sugata's place again!
That wasn't so bad.
Yo! Sugata!
Sorry to drop this
on you out of nowhere,
but do you mind if we
stay here for a while?
Sure, knock
yourselves out, you two.
Seriously? Score!
I can't guarantee
your safety, though.
Watch out! Behind you!
Bears are all over these
parts this time of year.
You really have
to watch your backs.
This sucks out
loud! I'm gonna die
a miserable
death if I stay here!
No way. You stay here and
you'll just go sifting through
my drawers looking
for panties or some crap.
I already said you
could stay at my place.
And get eaten by bears!
Yeah, whatever,
you probably deserve it.
You are such a witch!
Childhood friends should
help each other out, not
wish death upon each other!
Can you promise not to
steal my panties even if
you're in my room with
the perfect opportunity?
Uh... Sure.
You can count on me.
I don't buy it.
Isn't this some joyful banter?
What are we doing today?
Really? Well,
if that's the case
you're welcome
to stay at my house.
What?
I'll be the sweetest
host you could ever hope
to have keep you.
Her place is huge, right?
People are always saying it's
like the biggest one
in town or something.
Her family are the
big shots in Sorami!
And why not bring
along Sohara and Sugata
until your house
gets fixed. It'll be fun.
Now that sounds like the life.
We'll do it!
Excellent. Well,
that settles it then.
Why don't we get
your things moved in.
I'll be heading
back to my tent.
Dude! What's
your problem, Sugata?!
The mopey routine
just isn't your style!
Movin' up to the Big Time!
I am Mikako's father.
I invite you to stay with us
for as long as you wish.
The Satsukitane family has
been Sorami City's ruling clan
since way back in the Edo period
when it was just an inn town.
So that's what you meant when
you called her family big shots.
That's about the shape of it.
You guys look freaked. There's
nothing to be scared about,
I promise. As long
as you don't break any
of the very specific
rules, you'll be fine.
She's sorry!
Really, really sorry!
She's just a freakin' idiot.
Please spare her life, sir!
Hey, no big deal!
What are you all
doing standing around?
Hurry up and tend
to our honored guests.
Yes, right away, sir!
What a spread!
Sir, please try some of this.
Perhaps you'd
like some of mine, sir.
Have you noticed how they
keep calling Sugata "sir?"
Maybe... I dunno, 'cause
like, the Prez and him are
old childhood
friends or, I dunno...
Would you like to take a walk?
What, are you serious?!
Can't do this anymore.
I can't eat another thing.
Where's Master?
Ran off to take a bath.
Guess all that eating
got him all messy.
Seriously? He went to bathe?
Yeah, why, is that a problem?
No. But it could be. The
Satsukitane family has something
called the "Decapitation Bath."
It's open only to clan members.
He should be fine.
As long as Tomoki doesn't
try to enter
that particular bath.
Oh.
Hello... So you
wanna hop in with me?
I mean I don't mind. But
it might be kinda weird.
No! It's cool!
You're actually much more
forward than I would have
given you credit for.
I mean, just walking in here
the way you did...
N-No!
Sorry about this, though.
Gotta tell ya
somethin' serious.
You really should hurry up
and get the Hell out of here.
Before someone kills
you where you stand.
Oh, god!
Intruder alarm!
We have an intruder alarm!
There is an intruder in the
Decapitation Bath! After him!
There he is!
Get back here!
You really think
you can get away?!
These jerks
are gonna kill me!
Holy crap. Holy crap.
Mister, you gotta help.
Please don't let
those dudes kill me!
I am sorry, young man. But
no matter how close of friends
you are with my daughter, our
law on this matter is absolute.
Do it!
Tomoki!
Why is this happening?!
The Decapitation Bath
was originally a bath for
our ancestor,
a celestial maiden.
It was a place where she
could cleanse her divine robe.
But after her passing, the
bath was opened to the public,
and Sorami was
punished for doing so.
Earthquakes...
famine... tornadoes.
The disasters never ceased
until every single person
who had visited the
bath was decapitated.
Since that time, our
clan has had the honor of
watching over this bath
with utmost vigilance...
in order to protect
this fair town of Sorami.
Given his friendship with
Mikako, end his life quickly.
Sir.
You can't do this!
Mikako, please make them stop!
I cannot. Laws in the
Satsukitane family are absolute.
Nothing I say would change
their minds. But Sugata...
You might be able to.
Stop this now! If you take
one more step then I'll--
Oh, my young Sugata.
Do you intend on defying
the Satsukitane family?
This can't be happening.
No, please! Please
don't kill my friend!
You're in my way...
Take a hike, princess.
Stop this. What are
you doing to my Master?
I asked you a question, and
I expect a satisfactory answer.
Ikaros! Stop it, now!
I apologize for all the
trouble we've caused you.
Forget it. I'll overlook
everything that happened today
on account of that young lady.
It appears she's not someone
we should be taking lightly.
C'mon, let's get out of here.
Understood, Master.
And don't worry
about any of this.
I won't.
Mikako. I am going
to leave the rest of
this matter in your hands.
Thank you.
Rise and shine!
Good morning, everyone!
Yeah, good
morning to you, too.
We're almost there, so
you better wake the heck up.
Where?
To the uninhabited island.
What the Hell is going on?!
Wow, it's... Gorgeous!
This is a private
island owned by my family.
I want you all to treat
this place as your own home.
Just outta curiosity,
why'd you drag us to
the middle of nowhere anyway?
Because a certain someone
broke a sacred family law which
has made it all a wee bit tense
staying back at the main house.
I would've felt awful tossin'
you out onto the street,
so I brought you here
instead. I hope that wasn't
the wrong thing to do.
I could always take you back.
No, this is great.
Seriously, thanks.
You've gone really
far out of your way
for Tomoki, haven't you?
Tomo! You better show her
some pretty serious gratitude!
Thank you, Prez.
You're welcome, Tomoki.
Well, since we're here...
Let's go swimming!
Hold off for a second.
Don't underestimate
uninhabited islands.
Before anything, we need
to secure a food source
for our survival.
What? Mikako said this
is her family's island.
Isn't there some
kinda cottage or bungalow?
Actually we've
got nothing at all.
And that's our situation.
So we can't afford to
spend time sunning
and swimming.
Why don't we leave finding
the food to Ikaros and Tomoki.
The rest of us will head out to
look for fresh drinking water.
Sure, sounds good.
Hey, Ikaros.
Yes, Master?
Think maybe you should jump
in the water and catch us some
bream or tuna or something
tasty? Whadda ya say?
Yes, Master.
Make sure you catch some fat
ones with a lotta meat on 'em.
Yes, Master.
Cool! I found a coconut crab!
Coconut crab sounds awesome.
I've always wanted to try one!
Here goes!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
I don't wanna
eat you! I don't!
This sucks balls. On the
verge of death 'cause of
some stupid crab. Maybe
we eat vegetarian this trip.
Man, I'm freakin' starvin'.
Okay. Clearly these
mushrooms are a bad idea.
Oh, well... No choice.
No way, sista! Shut up!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Holy crap, musta passed
out after eatin' that thing.
What the Hell is this?
Save me!
So-Sohara?!
Oh my gosh, no! Sohara!
How did you get down
here?! Are you okay?
I'm glad you're safe.
I was starting to
get so worried about you.
What happened? I thought
you were with the others.
Where are they?!
I don't know what
happened to them.
Once we started running
we all got separated.
What's that?
That sound was chasing us,
so we ran as fast as we could.
I'm scared, Tomoki!
We'll find a safe place to hide
and sort out what's going on.
Calm down,
Sohara, I've got you.
'Kay...
We're gonna be fine.
When the sun comes up,
we'll go search for
everyone else. Cool?
Cool.
When morning broke,
we went looking for
Prez, Sugata, and Ikaros.
But one day turned into two,
then turned into three, four,
who knows how many.
We never found them.
At night, we kept
hearing that howl.
That awful, terrifying howl.
Tomo, what if
they're all dead?
What if they got eaten
by that horrible thing?
They'll be fine.
I just know it.
No way they'd
go down so easy.
Guess you're right.
I mean, I'm sure Prez
would've called for help
on her radio by now.
Yeah.
Check it out!
Wow! That's a pretty
big catch for breakfast!
Just hand 'em over
and I'll cook 'em up!
Cool. Sounds good to me.
You want one bowl or two?
And so, an entire month passed.
The two of us completely
readjusted to
life on the island.
Sohara even
started smiling again.
But just when I started thinking
it wouldn't be all bad if
things went on
like this forever...
What's the matter?
You all right?
I'm sorry... I just...
I started thinking about
everybody else
and got kinda sad.
It makes me wonder...
What's gonna happen if no one
ever comes to rescue us?
Will we just live here forever?
I guess we'll have
to make the most of
the time we have together.
Hm?
But with me here, at
least you won't be lonely.
And I promise you now,
you'll never be sad.
Thank you, Tomoki.
And you know... I'm
thinkin' life wouldn't be
near as depressing as
it is now if we had kids.
You wanna have kids?!
You mean like, now?
No! That's not what I was trying
to say at all! I meant, uh...
Um... Sohara...
I... It's okay, Tomoki.
We gotta get outta here!
Yeah!
Sohara!
Dammit legs, you have to move!
You hear me?! I said move!
Tomoki...
Don't worry about
me... I promise...
I'll be just fine. I will.
Sohara! I'm coming!
Let her go, monster!
Let go of her, dammit!
Let her go! Let her go!
Get your tentacles off
her, you damn dirty beast!
I have returned with a
fish, Master. I did not find
many schools of tuna out
here, so I crossed over to
the southern hemisphere
to find this one.
Tomo... I think... this is
just seaweed and oysters.
It's what?! So they were
just stuck all over Ikaros,
like barnacles or something?
Yes. As I walked
along the ocean floor,
all of that became stuck
to me for some reason.
So what was that blood-curdling
howl you let out?
And where are the others?
Master, do you wish
for me to check for
their life signs on my radar?
Yes! Please do.
One moment.
Ha! Now that's entertainment!
It's also your punishment for
breaking the rules of
my family. And with that,
I will exonerate you.
And I promise you
now, you'll never be sad.
Thank you, Tomoki.
Oh, to be young and in love.
Well... I think it had
more to do with the fact that
his life had
recently been spared.
You're telling me all
this crap. All this happened
because of something
Tomoki did again?!
Whoa! Just calm down, Sohara!
This whole thing
was your fault, Tomo!
You're the biggest
jerkwad on Planet Earth!
Somebody help me!
It's like my house never
even exploded! What the Hell?
Master, look over there.
Present Ikaros greeting!
Hello.
Please accept this
small token. A gift from the
entire Satsukitane
family... to you.
You may not have known this,
but strength counts for
everything in my family.
And it looks like
my father has grown
rather attached
to Ikaros here.
May I have your
attention, please.
Here's today's announcements:
And I promise you now,
you'll never be sad.
Thank you, Tomoki.
Next time... "Swimsuit
Surf Brigade, Go! Go! Go!"