Things are crazy right now,
I'm kind of overwhelmed.
The chain on my collar's been
cut. Which eliminates any danger
of the bomb inside of it from
detonating, so that's good.
But the moment that chain was
severed, so was the only thing
I ever truly had.
The connection to my master.
The only way an Angeloid finds
meaning in her existence is by
following her master's
orders to the letter.
But now, who do I obey?
What am I supposed to
do with this new life?
Maybe I should seek
out a new master.
I wonder what Tomoki
would think about that.
I will return to the Promised
Land! The girl's locker room!
What goes through
that head of his?
What are you up to?
Just building a new glider.
What's wrong?
I don't know what I'm supposed
to do with myself anymore.
I'm all alone.
I don't have a master.
And now you're a bird that
can fly freely through the air.
I'd call that a welcome
change from the norm.
Maybe.
You'll be fine. Give it a little
while, and I'm sure the answer
you need will come
to you in due time.
That means a lot. Hearing
it like that makes sense.
I think you may be right.
I hope you get to
fly soon, too, Sugata.
I told him we'd never go out.
Quantum conversion operating
at one hundred percent.
Metamorphosis stability:
all green.
At the present time,
everything is looking favorable.
How are you holding
up so far, Master?
"Favorable," yeah!
I might just start appreciating
the joys of being stepped on.
You sound just fine.
Perfect. This is exactly
what you should use the
greatest combat weapon ever
for. Doesn't what you're doing
seem the slightest
bit ridiculous, Alpha?
Master ordered me to do this.
And you seem to be enjoying it!
Which I guess isn't a problem.
I just wish I had some orders
from my master to carry out.
Tomoki.
Oh, hey. Is that you, Nymph?
I was just wondering if there's
anything I can do to help.
I got some free time.
Yeah, no. I'm good.
O-kay.
All right, Ikaros.
Time to transform me into
something else and move on!
So naughty!
Sorry to blow your
minds girls! Tomoko's back!
And now, it's
time to charge into
the Tennis Club's
locker room!
Crap! Why the
Hell's Sohara here?
Master. The Tennis Club
is still meeting in there
and she's a member.
Yeah, but that sucks!
As long as she's in there,
my peeping day is ruined!
She knows who I am.
I'm totally screwed!
Time for me to pitch in. I knew
if I stuck around long enough,
I'd be needed for--
No way. Everything up
to now has been a warm up.
That's all. The main
event is on its way.
You're not going
to give me an order?
I'm sick of gawking at bras
and panties all the time.
That's why my next target
is going to be a location like
you've never seen. A
paradise where even more girls
will be running
around half-naked!
Welcome to the
Satsukitane Swim Resort!
Please, make
yourselves at home.
What's mine is yours,
as you well know.
I had no idea your family
owned an indoor water park.
Seriously, that's
beyond awesome.
There are quite
a few people here.
Do you plan on changing
into a swim suit, Sugata?
Sorry. These are
the only clothes I own.
I have to say Sohara that's...
a big tube you have
wrapped around you.
Yeah, that's
because I can't swim.
If you'll recall,
neither can Ikaros.
An Angeloid's wings soak
up water, which become quite
heavy and weigh us down.
If that's the case, Nymph should
be able to swim just fine.
You don't have any
wings to get water-logged
so you won't
drop like a stone.
Don't make fun of me! I can
swim with or without wings.
So just shut up.
Let's see.
For your freakin'
information, Angeloids are not
designed to be able to swim!
Definitely not true.
Wow, is that true? Come to
think of it, where is Tomoki?
He was here
just a moment ago.
Where did he run off to now?
I mean, he was the one who
said we should all to go to
the pool together
in the first place.
I can't stand this any more!
All the smokin' hot bodies!
The slick-wet clingy swimsuits.
There's a richness you just
can't get from
bras and panties!
Tomoki!
Adios!
Where'd he go?
Prez! Look out behind you!
I've never been on
one of these before.
Guess I just jump in here.
Well, this isn't fun at all.
Anchors away.
I was right! This place
is paradise on earth!
Tomoki! What has
gotten into you?!
You're acting like a lunatic.
Uhhh. I'm-a so sorry, I
don'-a speak-a you language.
You don't speak the language?!
Whatever, my money says
you've been planning this
since before we even got here!
Hold up. Just
hear me out, would ya?
Look around you,
Sohara. Just look.
See all those faces?
They're happy!
Makes this argument seem
kind of silly, doesn't it?
I dunno. I guess, maybe?
Nothing but smiling faces...
at peace... And of course...
A veritable cornucopia of
butts and boobies bursting from
the confines of their suits!
Beautiful young women,
prancing about in public,
in broad daylight! Half-naked
of their own volition!
That's what the pool is!
If I can't come here to get
my fill of the female form,
then where would you
have me go?! Huh?! Where?!
What a bunch of
self-serving hokum.
I'd say it's almost
refreshing to see this
bold approach toward ogling.
If you'll excuse me.
Oh yeah, Sohara. If you still
wanna hit me, that's cool.
You just have to
come out here to do it.
Sohara, let me
handle this one.
What are you gonna do?
I don't care who you are,
you're taking this too far.
Commence Tomoki hacking!
What's this? I can't swim!
What's happening?! Help!
What did you do to me?!
Nothing special. I just
hacked your tiny brain
and put a block on all your
memories involving swimming
so you couldn't do it anymore.
Fascinating. So now
Tomoki will sink like a stone
anytime he gets in the water.
Now if you try any more of your
perverted crap, you could drown.
That's kinda funny.
Yeah. I think it's time for the
rest of us to enjoy ourselves.
What? Wait. Guys!
No, please! You can't
do this! This is cruel
and unusual punishment! Oh god.
Does this mean my days of
checking out half-naked
hotties are over?!
What's the point of even coming
to the water park anymore?!
"Dear Grandpa.
Here I am at the pool,
and I can't
even enjoy the ladies.
My life has lost any
semblance of meaning.
What do I do now?"
Master.
Hey, Ikaros.
Are you doing all right?
Doesn't matter. I'm
just gonna drift like this
for the rest of my life.
Wherever the current takes
me, that's where I'll go.
That slide is like a force
of nature it's so strong.
Duh! What's my
freakin' problem?!
Why am I so hung
up on swimsuits?!
Half-naked chicks
are all right, but...
Ikaros!
What is it Master?
I have an important
order for you.
You're lucky, Alpha, getting
to have Tomoki give you orders.
Isn't the current
moving kinda fast?
All is going according
to plan, Master.
Sugata, help!
Heads up! I'm tossing a line!
My swimsuit is coming loose!
Alpha's gotta be behind this!
Tomoki probably ordered her
to mess with the wave!
That's impossible!
My block in his brain
should still be in place.
How is he doing this?
Suits coming off, female
bodies thrashing about?
Your magic hoo-doo's nothing!
I just gotta copy what
I see them doing!
Oh, no! I'm not gonna make it!
I'm sinking! I'm gonna drown!
I don't wanna go out like this!
That's right, I forgot.
The lazy river is a circle!
I can just cruise
around all I like.
I don't have to swim at all.
I'm gonna drown!
Oh, yeah! Definitely drowning!
All right, Tomoki. Let's
think about this rationally.
It's a simple matter,
really. Whether I drown or
whether I don't. Whether
I live. Or whether I...
Tomo! Tomoki!
Whoa! Grandpa!
Tomoki. Go back.
It's not your time.
There's still
something you have to do!
Something I have to do?
Grandpa? Grandpa!
Master... Master!
I thought I was a goner!
Where did everyone go?
The pool was closed
after the incident,
so they went to go
change out of their suits.
No! They're changing?!
So that's it.
The pool day is over.
Thank you for the
second chance, Grandpa.
I swear, I will not let
this life be for nothing!
Thanks for waiting,
everyone. Here we go.
The ladies changing room at
the pool. The final sanctuary!
Inside waits a world
where bras, panties,
and swimsuits
are unnecessary.
Yes. Yes. Yeeessss!
Eeeee-yeeeessss!
This is my new form!
This is what I am now!
Here we go! She's putting
me on! She's putting me on!
I am climbing that
stairway to adulthood!
So! Which of these fine betties
is slipping me up her thighs?!
Okay this is weird. Were my
panties always so freakin' ugly?
Don't move! Don't you dare!
Move even a single
inch and your dead meat!
Master, if you get too worked
up, you know what will happen!
You're kidding me.
The scene was one far too
gruesome to call a massacre.
All that can reasonably be said
is we lost something that day.
Something sacred. And what
would that be, you ask?
I thought it was as
obvious as the sun in the sky.
We lost our greatest
warrior. So we thank him.
Thank you, Tomoki,
for giving us a dream.
Thank you for giving us hope.
Truly my friend,
thank you. Thank you.
It's just a
piece of junk now.
Sohara broke my
quantum converter!
You mean you still
haven't gotten your fill of
panties and boobs and stuff?
Hell no! How am
I supposed to peep on
the changing
rooms now?! Huh?!
There's always
Cool Guy Jamming.
If I invoke it, you can peep,
do whatever, and the girls
won't notice you any more
than the paint on the walls.
Then what are you
waiting for?! Invoke it!
Do it, please!
I'm begging you!
Sorry, not unless
you order me to do it.
Uh... Yeah. I dunno.
Come on!
Why?
It's just... with my master
gone, there's no one to
give me orders, so I'm
kind of wandering around
with no purpose. Please,
Tomoki, gimme an order!
I can't do that, Nymph.
How come? Don't you
have any orders for me?
I'll do anything
you need. Just tell me.
What do you want me to do?
You need to decide
that for yourself.
You can go wherever you want
now. Do whatever you want.
That's free will.
Welcome to it.
I just do, whatever
I want? Tomoki...
Okay, let's go over
the answers to the quiz.
Number one is
"the Pacific Rim."
She's being held...
by the sky.
She sent you an angel because
she wanted you to help her.
But that doesn't really matter
anymore. It's so interesting.
She's never seen an angel
enjoy herself so much before.
Or at all for that matter.
I came to you because I
wanted your help as well.
But I think I'll just go
to sleep instead. Good-bye.
Although, I do have
a favor to ask of you,
if you're willing to assist.
Don't forget about me.
Whatever you do.
Tomoki! Tomoki, come on!
Wake up, would ya!
Class is over
and you're drooling!
Oh, man. That dream...
What, same one as usual?
Yeah, angel was
babblin' somethin' to me.
Can't remember what.
Think it had anything
to do with Ikaros and Nymph
and all the craziness
they keep stirring up?
I don't know.
You don't know. Well if
you don't, who the heck does?
I don't care.
Look, it's whatever.
Nothing beats
my peace and quiet.
Long as you and me can
enjoy our time together,
it's enough for me.
Wow, I actually have
to agree with you for once.
Hey. What about you, what
kinda dreams do you have?
Like, did you
have one last night?
Last night?
Sohara...
Tomoki...
Oh, Tomo!
You rotten pervert!
No! It's way
too embarrassing!
Whoa, musta been
one heckuva dream!
Oh gosh, why would I even
have dreamt something like that?
Is it cause, someday, I might
actually want to marry Tomo?
Sohara...
Sorry I spaced out
there. We gotta roll.
Sugata invited us over to his
place after school, remember?
I totally forgot!
Wow. I can't believe it's
already been a whole year.
Another trial flight? You're
never gonna learn, are you?
Whatever. Good luck!
We'll be waiting down the way
a bit for whenever you crash.
Sugata, I have a question.
Why do you keep trying so hard
at this? I mean, you've failed
over and over again, right?
Because I had a dream once.
A dream where I soared
through the sky.
I know this will work.
A dream. That's nice.
And just one more
thing Angeloids can't do.
Dreams you have while sleeping
aren't the only kind there are.
You've got something
you dream about don't you?
Something that you
hope will come true.
Yeah, I guess I do. I really
want Tomoki to be my master,
but I try not
to think about it
because I know
it won't come true.
He told me I was free now,
and then he just walked away.
I dunno. Maybe
he doesn't like me.
It's the exact opposite.
That was Tomoki's
way of being nice to you.
That was... nice, huh?
So then that means he
doesn't hate me after all.
The wind's starting to pick up.
So are we go for launch?
We're "go." There's enough
wind for it, and while I'm not
perfectly happy with the
direction I'm about to go,
it shouldn't
affect my takeoff.
I wish you great
success in the sky.
I hope that somehow we all
get to see our dreams come true.
To a faraway new world!
He did it!
He's flying!
So hey, Alpha. Do you mind
if I stay here from now on?
I would like that.
Even though I might
take Tomoki away from you.
You're sure?
Of course. Whatever happens,
Master will still be my master.
From now into
eternity. Forever.
I had a
feeling you'd say that.
Tomoki... Sakurai...
What on earth was that?
"Heaven's Lost Property: Forte"