Okay, smile!
If you're still having
trouble with it, just fake it.
Just fake it?
That's right. Just pretend
so you know what it's like.
All right,
Master. How is this?
That's not what I had in mind!
What's going on in here?
I'm trying to teach
Ikaros how to smile.
How to smile, huh?
Well, you know she's
always going on about how she
wants to act more human...
I thought the first
logical step is to
learn how to smile.
Thing is you don't
have to really be happy to
pull off a smile.
It's perfectly cool to fake
one if you're not feeling it.
Watch me,
I'll show ya. See?!
Smiling.
No! You can't just
say it! Now try it again!
Grinning.
Dammit Ikaros, you're
just saying the words,
not making the face!
Smirking.
I came here with one goal in
mind. To take Alpha back, but...
During the Age of Exploration,
the Europeans discovered
the New World and embarked
on a policy of colonialism,
which then turned into
all-out global expansion.
Believe it or not,
even Japan felt the effects.
As such, a number of Japanese
were treated like slaves
and sent to Europe
against their will.
Toyotomi Hideyoshi, the ruler
at the time, saw this trend
and exiled the Jesuits from
the country. This is considered
to be the beginning
of Japan's isolationist era.
The slave trade was hidden
beneath the flashy façade
that was pushed
by Western diplomats.
These marauding expansionists
were indifferent to the people,
leading them like
cattle to slaughter
in order to satisfy
their own petty desires.
It's likely that within the
New World hovering above us
there exists a new breed
of slavery. One which seeks to
fulfill their own
inhabitant's unearthly desires.
Huh? You don't
know how to smile?
Yeah right? Go figure, you'd
think it would be easy for her.
Got any ideas how
we could teach her?
That's a tough
one 'cause smiling is
something we do unconsciously.
Oh, I know! Ikaros. Try raising
your arms above your head.
Above my head. Like this?
Banzai!
This is one of your
tickle zones, it should put a
big smile on your face! Doesn't
it make you wanna giggle?
What the--?! What the
heck is wrong with her?
Looks like it tickled her.
But it's not the
reaction I was hoping for!
That's because you
were doing it wrong!
Listen. Tickling
is an art form.
Take a lesson from the master!
This is the proper technique!
Coochie-coochie-coochie-coo!
Now this should tickle!
Oh, Tomo! Okay, Tomo. That's
enough. You can stop now.
Oh, this is gonna suck!
Quit molesting
me, you pervert!
I'm confused. I
don't know what it's
going to take to
make myself smile.
Hey, I know!
What? You don't
know how to smile?
I was thinkin' maybe you
could give her some advice.
Gee, Mister Takehara,
weird much?!
Yeah, right?!
I guess there's no point
in asking someone who
never smiles himself.
Come on. Let's go, Alpha.
Is there anything
I haven't tried?
Beats me.
Well what do we have here?
My favorite Angeloids,
Ikaros and Nymph.
So, you want to
learn how to smile?
Yes. I'm having a hard time.
So... Is there a specific
time of day you like to smile?
Or is there any
advice you could give us?
Let's see. Something that
always brings a smile to my face
is hitting someone
as hard as I can...
using a huge... flyswatter.
Stop it! I'm not a bug!
Tomoki?
Now that was funny as Hell.
I don't believe you.
How could you do that?
I'm sorry.
Oh please, Tomoki. It's
not like you were going to
die or anything,
who really cares?
I "really cares!" Ikaros is
a very impressionable person!
So did beating the
crap out of Tomoki get you
any closer to smiling?
Unfortunately, no.
Not yet, at least.
Oh right, I nearly forgot
what time of year it is.
It's almost Christmas.
Oh, I know! Why don't we
all get together this weekend
and throw a huge Christmas
party at Tomoki's place!
It would be so much fun!
But we all have to
pitch in for it to work.
Throw the best bash ever
and Ikaros has to smile!
Not bad.
That sounds like a plan.
You game, Tomoki?
What do you say?
I could get my mom to bake one
of her awesome cakes for us.
And we could put up a bunch of
decorations and swap presents!
Uh, sure. I guess that's okay.
Alright then. This Sunday,
consider it a date. Okay?
What's wrong?
Why can't I smile?
It is weird.
I mean I took off your
emotional protections
a while ago.
But you have to remember
you were created for combat.
Maybe you're just
physically incapable of it.
I was created as a...
combat-only model?
Well... Smiling's pretty
simple once you get down to it.
I wouldn't stress too much.
It's not simple. I mean... I
don't think I can even remember
the last time I saw you smile.
What? What are
you tryin' to get at?
You haven't seemed
happy for a while.
Really. It's not like you to go
this much time without smiling.
It's been... too long.
It's true, yeah. Angeloids
are not designed for smiling,
not unless we have
humans around who are
willing to help us learn.
And there's something
else. Lately I've been doing
a lot of worrying.
More so than normal.
But the part that's
troubling me the most is
I don't know
why I'm worrying.
Everything will be
okay! We'll just nip this
problem in the bud.
Let's brainstorm.
I'm sure we can find a way
to make you smile. Sound good?
Sure.
Oh, holy crap. I am so hungry!
Morning! How's it goin'?
Hi... Master.
Master. Good morning. Relax.
Easy, Tomoki. Calm down.
She has wings for
crying out loud! Wings!
Is something...
bothering you, Master?
What? No! I mean,
your boobs freakin' awesome.
I mean, what
the heck'm I saying?
Must... control myself!
You're blushing, Master.
Huh? Me?
Wait. What the
Hell is going on?
What happened to
your face? It's frozen!
Dang, it didn't work! We spent
all last night putting glue on
our faces to freeze our
expressions for nothing.
You guys are out
of your damn minds!
Come on, let's go
wash that crap off.
Don't think I
didn't see that smile
on your face, 'cause I did.
Oh shut the Hell up!
Ever since the accident I feel
like you're afraid to smile.
I... I know...
What if... I took you on a date?
We could do something simple,
like take a drive
in the country.
What is that
all about? A date?
Hey, Tomoki! I
have a great idea!
Oh?
We should all go on a date!
Whaaat?!
So, um... Do you even
understand what a date is?
Because most of the time.
it's something that a boy
and girl do together,
by themselves.
You mean we can't do
it with three people?
Well, we can
but it's not normal.
Then who cares? Don't you
remember what Sohara said?
If we do something fun
then the chances of Alpha
cracking a smile go
way up. She needs this.
What're we waiting
for? Let's do it!
A date with Master?
What is this feeling?
Am I actually... excited?
Ah, screw it. Come on,
ladies, let's get this
threesome on the road!
Yeah, so, what
do we do on a date?
Oh man, there's tons
of things you can do.
That's actually a
really good question which
I don't have the answer to.
Face it, Tomoki Sakurai.
You've never been
popular with the ladies.
But you can't let them know
this is your first real date!
Do not screw this up!
Gimme that! I gotta see!
"Try taking her shopping.
If you buy her something she
wants, her impression of you
will be very positive and
may lead to future intimacy."
Okay, my ladies! Anything
you want! I'll buy it for ya!
Jeez, Christmas really
snuck up on me this year.
Better start thinking of gift
ideas, for myself of course.
Master. I bought something.
Did you buy out the entire
freakin' grocery store?!
What about you, Nymph? Isn't
there anything you want to buy?
Figured you'd be all about it.
Yeah, I thought about it,
but I think I'm good.
And anyways, it wouldn't really
mean much. But thanks though.
"After shopping, you
can relax at a nice movie.
Try to pick a sappy one
for optimum emotional impact."
Bunch of stuff playing.
What looks good to you guys?
How 'bout this one?
No freakin' way!
Why not? It looks
right up your alley.
This one looks interesting.
'Kay. Ix-nay on the
oovie-may, what else is there?
"If a movie's not your style,
and depending on your budget,
you might try
an amusement park."
The mascots are
not a threat to us!
Maybe this wasn't
the best place to start.
Let's check out
some rides instead.
Master... is having fun.
The world's spinnin' so
fast I think my brain's
gonna fly outta my ears!
That was a huge mistake.
Whoa, are you okay?
I'm having fun on
my date with Master.
But still,
something is missing.
You pathetic baby.
Come on, let's get going.
There's more fun to be
had. Suck it up, Tomoki.
Initiating scan. All
systems read zero damage.
No faults in the
organic structure.
No reactor anomalies.
All systems green.
What was that just now?
It was almost...
like a quick twinge
of pain in my reactor.
Wow, they're amazing!
Oh, good. She's finally
chilling out a bit.
I'm gonna go see if I can
find some tea or something.
You guys take your time.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
I wish... Tomoki were
my Master. But... he's not.
Hey, Alpha. I don't
understand this place.
Why are all the
animals in cages?
I don't know.
Here's what I'm thinking...
Maybe this cage is kinda
like the chokers we wear.
If that's true, they want out.
Wouldn't you agree, Alpha?
If these animals could leave
their cages and roam free,
think about how
much happier they'd be.
What?
Y'know, Tomoki does
so much for us.
Would it make him happy
if we set them loose?
I don't know, would he?
Master... would be thrilled.
Alpha. What if we...
Alpha! What're you doing?!
Master would be...
happy. So happy!
Gotta love peace and quiet.
There's nothing better.
Nooo! Why do I get
the feeling my dates have
something to do with this?!
Hey, get back here!
This is your fault!
Master would be so happy...
Master would be...
so happy.
Calm down! Don't panic!
We'll return the
animals to their cages!
Hello, police! We have
a naked man running around
the park tampering
with all the cages!
All units, proceed
to the scene immediately.
We have multiple dangerous
animals on the loose!
Must be some
new kinda terrorism!
Everyone on high alert!
The little bastards
playing with us! Damn it!
Really pour it on boys!
We're takin' back the peace!
Earlier today, a nude man
wreaked havoc on the city zoo,
sending the patrons
and staff into a frenzy.
I always assumed he'd end
up doing something like this.
Though he was actually
a really nice guy.
If it were me, I'd give him
the freakin' death penalty.
I'm innocent!
I am very sorry
about all of this, Master.
I'm done with this crap
day, I wanna go home!
We did plenty of
date stuff, let's call it.
No way! There's so many
other things we want to do.
You wanna do
more? Like what?
Are you insane?!
It says right here if the date
goes well you're supposed to
kiss each other at the end.
Yeah, if it goes well!
And you're only supposed to
kiss one person, not two!
Oh... So only one
of us will get a kiss.
Hey, Alpha...
You mind if I try it?
That's okay. Isn't it?
Wait! Listen
to me, both of you!
Tomoki...
Hey! Hold on,
where you going?!
You can't just leave
me here alone with her!
Crap... What should I do?
No wait! Stop!
I was just kidding!
Jeez I can't believe
you fell for it.
What is this feeling? Is it
because I'm thinking of Tomoki?
It's so strange!
Are you okay? Nymph?
It's nothing! My reactor's
just actin' a little weird!
Keep your paws off me creep-o!
Why'd you have to hit me?!
I've done...
something horrible.
'Scuse me? Hey, wait!
I'm so sorry, Alpha. All
I wanted was to make some
memories for myself
before it was too late.
But I realized
that I have enough.
Reactor scan. Functioning
at one-hundred percent.
The time I've spent with
you two has been amazing.
Sure it was short, but so
sweet. And don't worry, Alpha.
Even if you can't smile, as
long as Tomoki is your Master,
he'll care about you more
and more each day. Forever.
My reactor must
be damaged. It hurts.
What is with you?
You up and fly away,
and you come
back totally filthy.
I'm sorry, Master.
And Nymph ran off pouting too.
What the Hell
is going on today?
Today was when I
went on my first date
and wasn't even
able to smile.
Come on. Let's go home.
The rules say the date
doesn't end until
I drop you off.
All right.
It looks like you're free
to roam now. Glad to see it.
So long you guys.
Tomoki. Alpha.
All right then.
Where should I go?
The sea? Or maybe a
deserted spot in the mountains?
I'm sure as long as I go
somewhere quiet and disappear,
no one will notice I'm gone.
Or maybe it would be
funny if I headed back to
the Synapse with,
oh I don't know,
a bomb or something like that.
Wonder what Master
would think of me then.
It's Gamma!
Next time...
"Queen of the Sky."