[EAGLE, LUNA panting]
Quick! We don't wanna
get there late.
Please. I can't run any faster.
[LUNA] Try. There isn't
gonna be any bread left
if we don't hurry.
That doesn't change how
fast I can run, y'know.
[LUNA giggles]
I think we can even afford
the good stuff today.
Yeah!
[LUNA]
It's so frustrating.
[EAGLE]
Huh?
Someday, I'll eat here
whenever I want to,
and no one will tell me "no."
Oh, come on.
Even you must know
that's impossible, Luna.
You're such a quitter.
How do you expect to win
if you give up before
the fight even starts?
We're not all as
stubborn as you are.
‐‐[BOTH] Huh?
‐‐[NOBLE 10A] What's this?
It appears a pair of
filthy street rats
are wandering where
they don't belong.
[NOBLE 10B]
At least use the bridge
so we're spared the sight
of your disgusting faces.
[LUNA growls]
Hmph. Just look.
It even snarls like a rat does.
Indeed, and it
smells like one, too.
The foul odor is making
me sick to my stomach.
Don't do it, Luna!
You're going to regret this.
Look, the rat can speak.
[LUNA] I've been studying,
and when I'm older,
I'm going to join
the Holy Church.
I'll become a Holy Maiden.
[gasps]
[LUNA]
And once I do,
I'll make you regret every
word you said to us today.
Have you lost your mind, girl?
Speaking to us like that‐‐
[LUNA]
Now, gentlemen.
I'd like your names, please.
[NOBLE 10A chuckles]
As if I would introduce myself
to garbage like you.
Hey, calm down.
You made your point.
They're leaving.
[LUNA] I refuse to lose
to people like that.
They'll see.
All of my hard work
will pay off one day.
[MESSENGER 10A]
Luna Elegant.
You have faithfully abided by
the teachings of the Cherub.
Putting into practice the
knowledge you've obtained
and are an age at which your
studies may begin in earnest.
As of today, you will officially
enter the Holy Church,
and train to become worthy of
being named "Holy Maiden."
Thank you.
It is an honor to accept.
Rise.
I would like to bring
my servant with me.
Perhaps you're aware?
Yes.
Well, it makes sense you'd
research Maiden candidates.
But I'm afraid the
servant you speak of
is no longer among us.
The execution's
been carried out.
[gasps]
[MESSENGER 10A] Your companion
was, in fact, a demihuman.
To think that such
a creature could
infiltrate the Holy Capital.
A‐‐ A demihuman?
No. Please wait!
Eagle never hurt
anybody, I swear.
Being a demihuman
is a sin in itself.
Are you or are you not striving
to become a Holy Maiden
of the Church one day?
[LUNA]
I am, but...
[MESSENGER 10A] In that case, I
would advise being more careful
with whom you
choose to associate.
[LUNA]
Eagle's dead.
The Holy Church says
that demihumans
can never be accepted.
And how can I go
against its teachings?
[LUNA] Two years later,
I became a Holy Maiden.
They allowed me to use "Light"
and even "Golden" magic
because they saw
my aptitude for it.
[LUNA] I was appointed to Rabby,
an impoverished village
inhabited by Bunnies who
were blessed by the Cherub.
[LUNA] If I'd been in
a position of power,
maybe I could have
found a home for Eagle
in a village like this,
and my friend would
still be alive.
O Cherub, please give me power.
[KUNAI]
Luna. Luna.
[gasps]
[LUNA]
Cherub?
[gasps]
[KUNAI]
Not quite.
Somebody's been
sleeping on the job.
Now, can you hear me? Luna?
[LUNA]
Oh, it was just Demon Lord.
Yes. I'm here.
What do you need?
[KUNAI]
What do you think I need?
I'm with Madam.
We're heading your
way, as planned.
Are you ready for us?
[LUNA]
Of course I'm ready, silly!
I was born ready!
"Ready" is my middle name!
[KUNAI] I see. Then obviously
I was just imagining you
talking in your sleep before.
[LUNA]
I don't know what you mean.
[LUNA chuckles]
[KUNAI]
Whatever you say.
I'm counting on you, Luna.
[LUNA]
You've got it!
Madam, you are about to
behold the main attraction
of our hot springs resort.
I've already witnessed
a man's eyesight
being miraculously
restored to him.
What other surprises do
you have in store for me?
Well, you'll see
for yourself soon.
What took you so long?
You slow poke! [giggles]
Come on! Hurry!
Goodness. You're even
pushier than usual.
What's gotten into you today?
[KUNAI] I'll leave you
ladies to it, then.
I hope you have a
relaxing experience.
I'm sure I will.
[LUNA]
Keep going, Madam.
We're almost there.
[LUNA]
Welcome to the public baths!
[SHRIMPFRY] You're telling me
this entire area is for bathing?
[LUNA]
Let's start by rinsing off.
My! Some sort of magic?
What is this contraption?
A shower. Nice, huh?
Please allow me to
wash your back, hop.
[SHRIMPFRY]
I've never felt so clean before.
It's like dirt I didn't
even know was there
is being washed away.
[LUNA] I know! Now that
I know what it's like,
I don't think I could
live without it!
I would be happy to
wash your hair, bunny.
[sighs]
We'll get you started
with a cleansing shampoo.
Then, after that, we'll
apply some conditioner
to moisturize your scalp and
repair the damage, bunny.
This is wonderful.
We could call it a day
now, and I'd be happy.
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Madam.
I haven't even begun
to show off my‐‐
I mean, that is,
there's still so much more
for you to experience here.
Just as self‐centered as ever.
I'm glad to see you
haven't changed.
Enough of this.
We're moving on now.
Coming, dear.
Well, what do you
think of this, Madam?
It's called a
carbon dioxide bath.
There's certainly something
peculiar about this water.
It's so strange.
But so good!
My body feels light and free,
like I could almost
float up into the sky.
Yep! And there's more!
Splash a little
water on your face
and tell me what you notice.
So smooth.
It's like a baby's bottom.
We're just warming up.
You ready to try the next one?
[SHRIMPFRY]
Oh! Slow down, Luna.
Running like this
is hardly dignified.
This one is the herbal bath.
What does the scent
remind you of?
It's a vibrant, woodsy aroma.
If I closed my eyes, I would
think we were in a forest.
Pretty amazing, right?
I don't know how he did it.
[SHRIMPFRY chuckles]
Oh, I see.
You sound like a woman
very much in love, Luna.
[gasps] In love?
What‐‐?!
What are you talking about?
No use pretending, dear.
I can see right through you.
You're positively smitten
with the Demon Lord.
That's ridiculous, Madam!
I'm not smitten with anyone,
certainly not that guy!
I hate to tell you this, but
he'll be a tricky one to catch.
You've certainly got your
work cut out for you.
I'm afraid your feminine charms
leave something to
be desired, dear.
Uh, okay, let's just move on
to the next room, shall we?
[SHRIMPFRY]
Why are you in such a hurry?
[LUNA] All right.
This is called a salt sauna.
Get ready to experience
the wonders of exfoliation!
Salt, huh?
[LUNA] First, you sit in
the heat for a few moments,
let a little bit
of sweat build up,
and then... See?
Gently rub the salt
into your skin.
We'll wait for a bit,
and then we'll wash it
all off in the shower.
Repeat as needed!
[SHRIMPFRY]
And it works?
Like a charm.
I did this yesterday,
and it was amazing.
I could practically
see the excess skin
falling right off my body.
See, the salt scrubs away
the outer layer of skin,
revealing a smoother
layer underneath!
I think it even toned my stomach
and thighs up a bit, too.
[SHRIMPFRY gasping]
Um, is something
the matter, Madam?
[SHRIMPFRY gasping]
[shrieks]
[SHRIMPFRY]
Hell yeah!
What‐‐ What's wrong?
Luna, dear. I've
made up my mind.
You have?
[WHITE] Madam Shrimpfry went to
Rabby Village for a vacation?
First he managed to lure
in our little sister,
and now he's sunk his devious
claws into Madam, as well?
[WHITE]
Queen, look at this!
So, a vacation, huh?
We care why?
[WHITE]
Because!
This is a significant
development.
It means he's making progress.
The Demon Lord's won
Madam to his side somehow.
[KILLER QUEEN]
What is your deal with this guy?
Come on, Sis.
He's just a shiny new toy
for Luna to play with.
[WHITE] Why aren't you
taking this more seriously?
[groans] 'Cause I saw
how our shithead sister
was acting in Yahoo.
I mean, wow.
It was almost sad how hard
the poor thing was trying.
That idiot is head
over heels in love.
In love with the Demon Lord?
That man is a threat
to our entire kingdom.
[scoffs] Can't say I'm surprised
that you don't understand.
Well, hopefully love
will find you someday.
I'll even pray for you
like a good Holy Maiden.
I have no use for your
sarcasm or your pity.
We need to have a
serious conversation.
O great holy someone
way up in heaven.
Yeah, I'm kinda
wingin' it, here.
I pray my big sister
isn't always unwanted.
One more thing.
My Zero.
Just let him know
that I love him.
I'm sensing this prayer
wasn't really for me.
Hell no.
You're just gonna admit it?
Oh, it's only you.
"Only"? Show a little respect.
I've been working hard
since this morning,
I'll have you know.
Is that a map of the village?
The facilities look like they've
been placed differently.
[TAHARA]
Yeah. That's 'cause they have.
[YU]
I see. Do you have a problem
with the way the chief
chose to arrange them?
Well, sometimes things
change and we need to adapt.
And not that you asked, but I
have the chief's permission
to shift the buildings around.
Oh. Looks great, then.
Gotta say,
you sure have changed.
Don't remember you being this
devoted to the chief before.
Like all you care about
is pleasing him.
It's strange.
The guy's not exactly
a spring chicken.
[TAHARA]
And the last time I checked,
your tastes ran in a
different direction.
There are all those bunnies
running around here, too.
[YU]
Hmm. I don't know why,
but lately all I can think about
is the chief and
making him happy.
Hey, you do you.
[TAHARA]
Please, stay like this.
A reasonably normal human
being, for all our sakes.
Looking at this,
it seems like you've got
a lot of changes in mind.
[TAHARA]
Yeah, kinda.
I was thinking about dividing
the village into sections
that serve different purposes.
Ya know what I mean?
There'd be a medical
section, a business section,
a visitors' section,
and a Bunny section.
A big revamp like
this one is gonna cost.
[TAHARA]
About that.
We'd be exchanging
your holy coin thing
for all the supplies
and labor we need.
Really? I'm so glad I could
contribute something.
[TAHARA] Totally. You shoulda
heard how happy the chief was,
talking about all the money
you're gonna bring in.
[TAHARA] Please, stay
like this. Just like this.
Seriously, I'm begging you.
But you know, Tahara.
If you're going to change
things up this drastically,
you might ask Madam
for some suggestions.
Not a chance.
Listen, think of this
place as our castle.
Madam gets no say in what we do.
This is our territory.
Some noble's not
calling the shots.
That'd set a
dangerous precedent.
Got it?
You say something
like that again,
I'll kill you.
Remember the Nightless
City incident.
I'm sorry.
It was a careless remark.
[TAHARA] Chief's planning to
go in the opposite direction
of the Great Empire.
I'm sure he told you that, too.
[YU]
He did.
According to him, going down
a well‐beaten path is boring.
Tell me, how do you
feel about that?
The thing is, Tahara,
I was touched by
the world fault.
Oh, great, there you go
again with the crazy talk.
[YU]
What's more, I've begun feeling
the presence of God
within the chief.
Okay, now you've really lost it.
Good one.
Whatja used to say?
Something about "unlocking
the body's mysteries"?
Is this the new
wacky catchphrase
you've decided to go with?
[YU]
No, it's not.
As time goes on,
that feeling only gets stronger.
Surely you can sense the
truth, too, if only vaguely.
I'm not quite sure
why we're doing this
when I'm perfectly healthy.
Because everyone needs
regular checkups
to make sure their bodies
are functioning properly.
What if there is something wrong
and you simply don't
realize it yet?
Okay, that's fair enough.
You have a point.
[panting]
Yeah, actually,
I think I'm gonna go.
Promise I'll come by if I get
so much as a sniffle, though.
‐‐Sorry.
‐‐But you mustn't go, Chief.
You examination isn't over yet.
You might have a fever.
Your chest is so hot,
and so hard, and so smooth.
[YU gasps]
Chief!
Really, I'm done.
I've got pressing business
matters to see to.
I'm sure there's
nothing wrong with me.
Boo! No fair.
[YU gasps]
[sighs] This is the life.
Ha, ha. There's
nothing quite like
an outdoor bath in
a fantasy world.
[TRON]
I finally found you.
[KUNAI]
Dammit, runt!
What the hell are
you doing out here?
You deserve to be
pampered a little,
so let me wash that long hair
of yours while you relax.
Would you get out of here, runt?
This is the men's bath!
Stop calling me a runt.
Use my name for once.
If the others saw you out here,
they'd never let me
hear the end of it.
Leave already!
You're not even wearing a towel.
I don't have a problem with
Zero seeing me like this.
I am not Zero!
And don't ever call me
that with people around!
[TRON]
Uh...
All right.
If that's what Zero wants, this
will just be our little secret.
[KUNAI]
Enough about Zero.
Come on. I'm getting
you out of here.
[TRON]
Oh, my.
Well, it's no real surprise
the TV doesn't work.
[OONO] If this were the
same as Infinity Game,
the dining room would
be fully stocked,
and steamed buns would
automatically appear
in the guest rooms.
[OONO] I guess we're out of luck
as far as food is concerned.
[OONO]
The toiletries all seem to be
replenishing on
their own, though,
so I guess that's
something, at least.
[door opens, closes]
[AKU humming]
Demon Lord!
You weren't kidding about how
incredible this resort would be.
Really. It's perfect. All of it!
Glad you're enjoying
yourself, Aku.
Today I got to try something
called an herbal bath.
Now that you mention it,
you do smell fresh and herby.
[AKU]
I do? Really?
Guess you're sleeping
with me again.
[sighs]
[footsteps]
[LUNA]
Aku!
You were supposed to be my
snuggle buddy tonight, remember?
Hey, keep your voice down.
She's already asleep.
You filthy, rotten pervert!
What exactly are
you up to in here?
I don't know what kind of gross
stuff you might be imagining,
but I'm trying to get some sleep
after a long day of work.
[gasps]
[LUNA]
Fine. You leave me no choice.
I'll have to sleep in here
and keep an eye on you.
This might be the softest bed
I've ever felt in my life.
I'm never leaving.
[LUNA gasps]
Hey! Hands to yourself!
You totally tried to grab my
butt just now, didn't you?
How many times do I
have to tell you:
I have no interest in
grabbing your butt.
There's no use denying it.
Clearly, I'll have
to keep a watch on
this naughty hand of yours.
[KUNAI]
Come on.
[sighs] It doesn't make
a very good pillow.
It's all hard, and I can
feel your veins throbbing.
[KUNAI]
I know you could have found
a better way to phrase that.
[AKU]
Demon Lord!
[KUNAI] Huh? Your voice
sounds weird, Aku.
You got a cold?
[LUNA] Ugh, mine sounds
all funny, too.
[TRON]
Same here.
[KUNAI] Hold on, why are
you all dressed like boys?
[YU]
It's your turn, Chief!
I have the perfect
outfit for you.
Please just give it chance.
You're going to look so cute!
So cute! So cute!
[OONO]
So cute!
Wait, what was that dream?
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 11.
"Yukikaze Attacks."