[KUNAI]
Last time on Demon Lord, Retry.
[growls]
No, no! Please! I beg you!
I don't wanna be killed
by a human in this place!
Huh?
I'm sure you've done
your share of killing.
You should get to experience
what it's like to die for once.
It's only fair, right?
[CARNIVAL screams]
[CARNIVAL gasps]
What filthy fireworks.
[thud]
[UTOPIA] What in the world
happened out there?
They unleashed it
much too early.
What were they thinking?
That damn Merge must
have lost his mind.
I'm not sure.
I assume something unexpected
must have come up.
Well, then.
What you must do is take that
and tell them to unleash
the remaining two at
the Holy Castle, Tron.
I'm sure even you
can manage that.
Filthy mixed‐blood that you are.
Yes, sir.
Get out of my sight.
You're an eyesore.
[KAMIYA]
Look, loves!
A beautiful flower
for a beautiful crowd!
[PATRONS cheer]
Artemis is on a different level.
Look at this,
they even hired a clown
to keep the guests
calm in crisis.
That's right, because
after all, as nobles,
it's our responsibility
to set the example
and maintain decorum.
[KAMIYA]
What a fool of a Holy Maiden.
Showing up here
without even an escort?
And there's the queen
of high society,
Shrimpfry Butterfly.
She has a keen eye,
a strong instinct with people,
and crazy good
connections far and wide.
As far as the others go,
I assume they're the
Holy Maiden's friends.
But my target is Luna Elegant.
I'm afraid the
Satanists have decided
your time has come, my dear.
[LUNA] I don't get it. He said
he'd be right back, didn't he?
So, what the heck is
taking him so long?
I know, but don't
worry, Sister Luna!
Demon Lord's never broken
a promise he's made to us,
and I don't think
he'll start now.
For my money,
Aku is probably right.
Let's just be patient and wait.
[KAMIYA]
Oh, my!
What a fine collection
of gorgeous individuals
we have here!
You sparkle and
shine so brightly,
I'm absolutely dazzled!
I think this clown's
specialty is flattery.
I almost hate to ask,
but mind if I show off
a little trick of my own?
Come on! Cut me a break.
How can someone as pretty
as you do tricks, too?
I mean, how is that fair?
[slicing]
[KAMIYA]
Wait, what?
Are those... my...?
Sorry, did you happen
to drop your left arm?
Or perhaps, maybe your right?
Both. I lost both
it would appear.
Well, that seems like
quite the predicament!
But, tell you what, I'll do you
a little favor just for today.
[shrieks]
Oops, sorry, my bad.
Unfortunately, it seems I
accidentally mixed up your arms.
Are you serious?
This is not a laughing matter!
I've seen my fair share of
magic tricks in my time,
but I'll admit, I haven't
the faintest idea
how you pulled that one off!
I'm so pleased that you
enjoyed it, dear Madam!
I'll do better, though.
This time, they'll go to
the right place. [giggles]
You‐‐You did it!
My arms are back!
It's a miracle!
Be careful not to
drop them next time,
Mister Clown.
By the way, about that
poison in your pocket,
it has quite a smell.
If you really want
to kill someone,
you're gonna have to do a heck
of a lot better than that.
[YU chuckles]
[KAMIYA gasps]
[YU] And if I ever see you
again, I'll slice you up alive.
Got it, clown?
You take care!
[KAMIYA shrieks]
[BOTH panting]
[KILLER QUEEN grunts]
[FUJI grunts]
[KILLER QUEEN yells]
Sister, looks like our
work's been cut out for us!
Moron.
Are you here just to say the
most cliché shit possible?
Wow, look at those muscles.
Well what do you say,
you big, burly man?
Wanna come and play?
[HANITORA 07B groans]
[KILLER QUEEN] You stink like
the sack of shit you are!
Sprint for me,
my fastest fingers.
Drag Car, go!
[HANITORA 07B groans]
[gasps]
Back to the sewer and [bleep]
off, you nasty [bleep] [bleep]!
You killed my little sister!
I'm gonna make you pay for that!
[screams]
Ahh. That sure was a nice one!
When compared to your
prowess on the battlefield,
I'm afraid this old guard will
always seem woefully lacking.
Well, I mean, duh.
'Cause you're ancient,
you damn grandpa.
Come forth, o' abysmal darkness.
Shower the world with mourning.
Summon Holy Rain!
[SATANISTS scream]
[MINK giggles]
You sad, feeble little humans.
When faced with my darkness,
you're powerless, aren't you?
I'll turn you into my puppets
and you'll fight for me
until you crumble!
Bubble Cure!
Oh, Lady Mink,
we are so grateful!
That's an S‐Rank
Adventurer for you, huh?
Except... what are all of those
sinister‐sounding
incantations about?
Remember, she's elite enough
to be called a star player.
I'm sure she has her
reasons for what she does.
I order you to follow me.
It's time to shed your blood
for the chilling darkness!
[PRIESTS mumbling]
Give me a break.
What is she even
fighting against, anyway?
Well, judging by
the looks of it,
I take it you got
roughed up pretty bad.
Yeah.
[SATANIST SCOUT 07A coughs]
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
But Merge and the rest...
All of them have been
killed in battle.
What? Impossible!
Explain yourself, now!
[SATANIST SCOUT 07A]
The Demon Lord...
[SATANISTS murmur]
[SATANIST CAPTAIN 07A]
Hm?
Now that it's come to this,
seems we have no choice.
[SATANIST CAPTAIN 07B]
Yes, and may disaster befall
this cursed land!
[SATANIST CAPTAIN 07A, 07B]
Now, Summon Devil!
[SATANISTS]
Summon Devil!
[SATANISTS groaning]
[SATANIST CAPTAIN 07C groaning]
[ORUIT]
Wonderful.
What an annoying place
I've been summoned to.
A divine barrier, huh?
[ORUIT]
Hmm.
This evil power.
Is it... a Head Devil?
Protection of the Seraph!
Angel Veil!
Well, this place is
truly unpleasant. Hmm.
Whoa, it's the prince!
What the hell is
going on around here?
Even better, the angels sent
some of their dogs to play.
Sister, you can leave him to me!
Don't! Fuji!
[FUJI groans]
You okay?
[KILLER QUEEN grunts]
[ORUIT] Forgive me,
but I refuse to believe that
ants like you can actually
walk on two legs.
Summon the Killing Field.
[WHITE]
It's taking everything I've got
just to protect the Holy Castle.
Shall I finally break it out?
[KILLER QUEEN grunts]
[FUJI]
Thank you, Queen!
[MINK] You're the Prince
of Darkness, I presume?
It's just as I thought.
It's simply the fate of darkness
to be drawn by other darkness.
The lousy holy powers keep
coming one after another.
[KILLER QUEEN yells]
Hey, don't you dare
even try to look away!
I'm here!
[KILLER QUEEN grunts]
[ORUIT groans]
[KILLER QUEEN grunting]
[MINK grunts]
[MINK groans]
I have never seen such
uncivilized women.
Black Eraser!
All right, protect me!
Light Wall, up!
[KILLER QUEEN groans]
[MINK yells]
[chuckles] I should
tell you about
my favorite weapon,
named Twinkle.
It denies the very
existence of evil beings!
[chuckles] Guess that's not
bad for Miss Giant Jugs.
Excuse me? Did you say "jugs"?
[BOTH gasp]
[ORUIT]
Hmm.
[KILLER QUEEN]
Damn, not Hades again!
[MINK]
This is crazy.
What would Hades be doing
in a place like this?
[gasps]
Poor, filthy little humans.
[groaning]
[MINK yells]
[ORUIT grunts]
[MINK groans]
This is the end for you.
Come forth, Ray of Darkness.
[BOTH scream]
Such lowly, pathetic creatures.
[BOTH groaning]
[WHITE]
Queen!
No, you have to stay back!
You must maintain the barrier!
But, sister!
[OONO] You've got to be
freakin' kiddin' me!
This situation's
totally ridiculous,
not to mention her outfit.
Is she the other
Holy Maiden or what?
She's outrageously
beautiful on the outside,
but if she's
related to those two,
she's definitely gotta be
some kind of messed up.
‐‐[ORUIT grunts]
‐‐[KILLER QUEEN gasps]
[gasps]
Now, human.
Shall we go ahead and
begin this lovely feast?
The sin of annoying me is grave,
and you'll pay accordingly.
[OONO]
You asshat!
I was just about to start
studying the Seraph,
and of course you showed up
before I got to it.
Well, I'm not gonna let
some damn monster like you
get in my way, that's for sure!
Wait, I know!
I can maneuver things around
so he has to deal with
a whole other obstacle!
[KUNAI grunting]
[gasps]
[ORUIT]
Hm.
[WHITE]
What is this light?
[KIRISAME]
Huh?
Zero! [blubbering]
[KIRISAME]
Hm?
Hey, what's your deal?
Every time I see you,
you're getting bullied.
You... came to help us again?
[KIRISAME]
This another new arena
of that underwhelming empire?
Got some weird
monster here, too.
[ORUIT]
Hmm.
[KILLER QUEEN groans]
Bastard.
Where did you come from, anyway?
Wow, you smell like crap, man.
That's the scent
of a real murderer.
[ORUIT grunts]
[KIRISAME grunts]
[hisses]
Shut your mouth!
[KIRISAME]
Hmph.
[ORUIT]
Hm?
[KIRISAME] I'm the very
definition of "unrivaled"!
I've found my truth down
the path of carnage!
What absolute filth.
Saying an incantation‐‐
[KIRISAME grunts]
[ORUIT gasping]
[ORUIT yelling]
[ORUIT groaning]
You're a scumbag
who makes women cry.
Well, I'm about to teach you
how weak you really are!
Come on, who gave you
permission to lie down?
[ORUIT screams]
Heh. Man, that's just sad.
Look at you, wailing
like a little child.
Shut your mouth.
You're nothing but trash!
Come forth, Ray of Darkness!
[ORUIT gasps]
[KIRISAME] What kinda weak trick
was that supposed to be?
Listen, and don't take
this the wrong way,
but can you afford
to mess this up?
No way, you've got
to be kidding me.
Huh?
[gasps]
I won't go down like this.
Not someone as great as me!
Oh, no! [gasps]
Ugh. Your blood is disgusting.
I can't stand the stink.
[TRON gasps, groans]
[footsteps]
[TRON]
I wonder, for what purpose
was I even born in this place?
[KIRISAME]
Hurting some poor kid like that.
Hey, runt, you alive?
Come on, open your eyes!
Kid! You hear me?
You're still in there, right?
[TRON hiccups, gasps]
[TRON]
Huh?
[KIRISAME] That was one of my
most prized recovery items!
You should be just fine now.
But the wound.
It's gone.
You're a gloomy one, runt.
I just saved your life.
Think you could
manage one smile?
Oh, right, a smile.
It's been so long
that I forgot how to.
[ORUIT] What in the world
is that healing power?
Don't tell me he's
a new race of dragon.
This is dangerous,
too dangerous!
Well, if that's really the case,
I vow on my soul to kill
this dragon no matter what!
[ORUIT growls]
You piss me off, Dragon.
Now, I will judge you.
Your arrogance will be punished.
[TRON gasps]
[KIRISAME]
I recommend smiling, runt.
[TRON gasps]
[KIRISAME]
No matter how tough it gets,
the ones who keep
smiling like idiots‐‐
they're stronger
than anyone else.
[TRON gasps]
Dragon! This is the end
of your arrogance!
Say goodbye to this world!
[KIRISAME]
Heaven! Watch and learn!
All or nothing!
[KIRISAME yelling]
[ORUIT growling]
[ORUIT roars]
[AKU]
Demon Lord! Watch this!
[KUNAI]
Hmm? What is it?
[AKU]
Ahem!
"I'm the very
definition of unrivaled!"
[KUNAI]
Huh?
[AKU] "I've found my truth
down the path of carnage!"
[KUNAI]
What is this?
[AKU]
"Heaven! Watch and learn!"
[KUNAI]
Stop!
[AKU]
"All or nothing!"
[KUNAI] I think someone put her
up to this like last time.
[AKU] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 8.
"Demon Lord's Handiwork."
[KUNAI]
Whoever you are, show yourself!