[WHITE]
It's you?
[KUNAI]
Mm? Hello there.
Seems our humble resort
has an exalted visitor.
[WHITE]
What is this?
Did you and your minions
arrange for an ambush?
The tranquility of this
outdoor bath is a sacred thing.
The only people who would
ever cause trouble here
are children who
don't know any better
and uncivilized fools.
And I would like to
believe you don't fall into
either of those two groups.
[OONO]
I need to calm down!
If I do something that
inadvertently makes her scream,
and someone hears it,
my name and reputation
will be destroyed!
It's like riding on a
crowded train, for example.
Why is it that,
for no damn reason at all,
people automatically assume
that if you're a man,
you have to be a bad guy?
[sighs]
[OONO] They can't throw me
in jail for something stupid
like ogling a
Holy Maiden, can they?
That'd be ridiculous.
[OONO]
Shit!
Why can't I just take a bath
without some kind of trouble
following me into the water?
What's a Holy Maiden doing
in this village, anyway?
And in the men's bath,
of all places?
[OONO] Oh, no! Could this
be some kind of honey trap?
Wait.
Even if they had set a trap
for me like that somehow,
there's no way a woman
who's considered
the pinnacle of the kingdom
would lower herself
to participate.
If you've traveled all
this way to find me,
then I assume it concerns some
matter of great importance.
And, believe it or not,
I am actually willing to
lend you an open ear.
A matter of importance?
I'm here because of
what you've done to my‐‐
Before we go there,
I find your appearance
incredibly vexing.
[WHITE gasps]
[KUNAI] I recommend you
cover up with this.
[WHITE gasps]
Wait!
Are you saying you were
staring at me naked?
[KUNAI]
How about you just go ahead
and get into the
bath already, okay?
You're a very important person.
If you were to catch a cold,
the whole kingdom would suffer.
[WHITE]
Why?
This is the first time a
man has ever seen me naked.
And on top of that, he said
my appearance was vexing!
[KUNAI]
Now, then, let's hear about this
important of business of yours.
[WHITE]
So, what is he saying?
That my naked body isn't
even worth looking at?
Well, Demon Lord,
it's bad enough that Mada...
[WHITE gasps]
[sighs] What's wrong
now, Holy Maiden?
I mean,
it can't be that the
representative of your kingdom
would be so adorably coy,
as to get flustered
by the mere sight of a man
in the nude, could it?
[OONO] No, it's fine.
It doesn't matter.
Who cares, right? No biggie.
It isn't like seeing a naked man
is some crime of indecency
or anything, right?
[WHITE]
And this is the first time
I've ever seen a naked man, too.
Why did it have to be the
Demon Lord, of all people?
The epitome of evil right here
in the bath with me, naked!
U‐Uh... Oh?
Why, yes, you are
also in the nude.
Well, seeing you that way
means nothing at all to me.
I'm relieved to hear that.
This means we can converse
calmly without any awkwardness.
All right, then.
So what are you trying to do?
Deceive Madam and
upset the kingdom?
Well, there you go, bringing up
deception and making it awkward.
To set the record straight,
both Madam and Luna wish
to stay in the village
of their own free will.
I am not forcing anyone to do
anything they don't want to do.
Give me one reason why
I should believe you.
I'm waiting!
I would appreciate it if you
came no closer than you are.
I can't help but find your
body rather stimulating,
if you must know.
Uh‐‐How much more do
you plan to insult me?
Will you not be satisfied
until you bring me to tears?
You misunderstand me.
I was being utterly sincere when
I said to keep your distance.
I'm not in the business
of telling lies, you know.
[WHITE]
You expect me to believe you're
telling the truth right now?
I can show you why
Madam chooses to stay.
A quick soak in this bath should
answer that question for you.
How can taking a bath
answer anything at all?
[KUNAI]
Why don't you just relax
and get in up to your
shoulders, at least?
[OONO]
That's better.
Focus hard enough and you
can ignore any distraction.
My mind is a blank slate.
I'm filled with nothingness.
[gasps] This bath is just so...
Ah! My shoulders!
[gasping]
[OONO]
Hey, quit with the sexy sounds!
And stop using that
cute voice, will ya?
[panting]
What's happening right now?
This is a total first
for me! [gasps]
[OONO] Gah! You're
torturing me on purpose!
[KUNAI]
This outdoor bath is great.
It helps with more
than just exhaustion.
It also has the power
to set you free from
the pressures of
your everyday life.
You can forget all your troubles
and get a momentary
sense of release.
It's highly restorative
and can help you get your
strength and vitality back,
so you can face another day.
Sets you free from
life's pressures?
[KUNAI] The pleasant
feeling you're experiencing
in this water is the
answer to everything.
Oh. Are you saying that I
should drink that beverage?
[KUNAI] Are you really so
frightened of the Demon Lord
that you'd refuse
my hospitality?
You are the pinnacle
of the kingdom,
and this display of
cowardice and over‐caution
might be one of the
reasons this land is in
such terrible disarray,
don't you think?
[gasps] You have no
right to speak to me
in such a disrespectful manner!
Besides, if you believe that
you can poison me so easily,
you're mistaken.
Angel's Spoon.
[KUNAI] If you ask me, the worst
poison in this entire kingdom
is the people who are
in charge of running it.
[KUNAI] They don't care about
the poor and hungry masses
living their miserable lives.
They just turn
their backs on them.
They don't lift a finger
to address the problem,
nor do they feel the
need to develop a plan
to offer aid to the
people who suffer.
In my country,
we call people like this
incompetent despots.
[gasps]
[WHITE]
I can't even argue.
Well, from your perspective,
I can see how it
might seem that way.
Witnessing a young woman in my
position spinning her wheels.
It must appear so absurd.
[OONO] Her beauty alone could
stop men dead in their tracks‐‐
like some femme fatale.
Although, I guess in this world,
they'd probably just
call her an angel.
[sighs]
[WHITE gasps]
This is a popular drink
from my country.
It's been beloved by my
people for centuries now.
[gasps] Indirect...
Were you going to
say indirect kiss?
What are you, a child?
Only a young girl would
say something so immature.
[WHITE]
I hope you can forgive me.
Yeah, I'm kinda wingin' it here.
I pray my big sister
isn't always unwanted.
I'm sorry for being so immature.
But so what? I am young, y'know?
Hold on. I'm not saying acting
young is bad, or anything.
In fact, women who seem innocent
are typically really popular.
I think you should be
proud of who you are.
[WHITE]
What? How could I ever be proud
of something like that?
You're sitting there ridiculing
and laughing at me for it!
I'm not ridiculing you at all.
I mean, I for one find
your stubbornness impressive.
[WHITE] I'm sick and
tired of hearing about
how hard‐headed I am!
Don't treat me like I'm
some intractable brat!
[OONO]
Gah! I walked into a minefield!
There's no saving my ass now!
So, it's come to this.
Huh? What in the world is that?
Because you have upheld
the Holy Maiden name,
I would be honored to
bestow this upon you.
[WHITE gasps]
[KUNAI]
I only ask that you never
bring shame upon this halo.
And please remember:
I am not your enemy.
[gasps]
[WHITE]
Huh?
An Angel's Halo?
Why would the
Demon Lord have this?
[OONO] I just need to get Her
Holy Maiden‐ness home safely
and I can go about my business.
[KUNAI]
Hm?
[OONO]
She's still wearing it?
Well, I guess it suits her.
Holy Maiden White.
Did you travel here from
the Holy Capital by carriage?
No, I didn't.
You came alone, then?
That's right.
[WHITE] I can't speak of the
Seraph's Miracles to anyone,
and certainly not to a man who
may be a threat to the kingdom.
Very well. Then, please allow
me to escort you back home.
Huh? That won't be necessa‐‐
[WHITE gasps]
Excuse me.
I'm not entirely
comfortable with this.
I promise, there's
no need to worry.
Just relax and leave
everything to me.
"Just relax"?
Will you please
explain what's go‐‐
Quiet, now.
It would be best if you remained
silent for what I'm about to do.
O Wings, carry me
far from this place.
Instant Movement: Holy Castle.
[WHITE] That transported us
just like Seraph's Bound would.
A Miracle!
That had to be the
work of an angel.
What are you, exactly?
Do you remember what I said
to you the last time we met?
About how seeing
something in person
is always better than
having it explained to you?
[gasps]
You confronted me, and I
returned you home safely.
I'll let you assess my actions
and draw your own conclusions.
But just so we're clear,
you're to tell no one
about what happened today.
Of course.
[WHITE] Even if he hadn't
warned me not to,
I wouldn't dare speak
of this to anybody.
[WHITE]
News of what he did
might well plunge the
entire kingdom into chaos.
That a Miracle left
behind by the Seraph
could be used by somebody else.
[WHITE]
That there exists a person
who can bestow a
halo upon others,
when it was believed that
only angels could wear them.
I don't understand.
Who in the world are you?
[KUNAI] Hmm. I suppose I'd
say I'm someone who's hoping
he can count on your
cooperation in the future.
As I mentioned before, I'd like
to learn more about the Seraph,
and I think you can
help me with that.
Okay, but why the Seraph?
Because, you see,
I was called here by the Ophan.
The Ophan summoned you?
[WHITE]
If that's actually true
and not part of
some devious plot,
it would explain so much!
[WHITE]
That could be why Luna is drawn
so strongly to someone
like the Demon Lord,
despite her deep
devotion to the Cherub
and her utterly
self‐centered nature.
And why strong‐willed
Madam left the interior
in favor of Rabby Village.
[WHITE] And how he can use a
Miracle, just like the Seraph.
It explains why he can give
someone an Angel's Halo
when such a thing
should be impossible.
[WHITE] And that mysterious
building with the sacred baths.
I must know.
Do you seek information because
you mean to oppose the Seraph?
I assure you that is
not my intention.
There are just a few questions
I would like to have answered.
[WHITE gasps]
I‐I, uh...
[KUNAI]
Hmm, nice.
Perfect.
I suspected an Angel's Halo
would look good on you.
[gasps]
[KUNAI]
Let's meet again.
[WHITE gasps]
[KUNAI]
Holy Maiden White!
[WHITE]
Lucifer.
According to legend, he was a
fallen angel and a demon lord.
[WHITE]
An Angel's Halo.
Something sacred and beautiful.
Surely, the one who made this
couldn't be an evil being.
[WHITE] Someday, I'll help
you revert to the angel
you truly are.
[AKU] Demon Lord,
I was looking for you!
Found me.
It's good to see you.
Listen, Aku.
You really need to
be more careful.
You can't go around sitting
on men's laps all the time.
You're just so
innocent and trusting,
and frankly, it's going
to worry me sick.
[AKU]
That shouldn't be hard.
I don't even think about getting
close to other men besides you.
[KUNAI]
Oh, really?
I guess it's fine, then.
Yeah!
[KUNAI chuckles]
[AKU giggles]
[AKU] I heard you're
taking a trip tomorrow.
Going up north.
[KUNAI]
You heard right.
But I can always use Instant
Movement if I need to.
A trip I can return
from at any time
can hardly be called
a trip, can it?
True.
But I might get lonely.
Ah. I'll see if I can't
find you a special souvenir.
To cheer you up a little bit.
Demon Lord.
Please promise me you'll
come home safe and sound.
[KUNAI chuckles] Who do you
think you're talking to, huh?
[giggles]
[LUNA] Aku? What are
you doing out here?
Luna won't stop whining.
Aku and I were just having
a little chat, that's all.
You... You‐‐!
You damn pervert!
My butt wasn't enough for you,
so you had to go for Aku's, too?
By the way, I made sure
your sister got home safely.
I escorted her back to the
Holy Castle myself, in fact.
[gasps] Just great!
So now you've got your claws
in my sister, as well?
[TRON yawns]
All of this screaming is
really wearing me out.
[KUNAI, AKU, LUNA chuckle]
[OONO groans]
How did I end up like this?
[OONO] I'm never gonna
be able to sleep.
I'm not a damn teddy bear!
[KUNAI] Yu, you're in
charge of the hospital.
Do what you can to build our
reputation while I'm gone.
Of course.
Just leave everything to me.
[YU gasps]
Hold on. Here.
Your tie.
Tahara, Rabby Village and
its people are in your hands.
If there's an emergency,
you can send a message
to me at any given time.
Yeah, I got it.
But I seriously doubt
anything will come up
that I can't handle
without your help, Chief.
Heh.
[OONO]
Look at this place.
The village is changing.
It's come a long way,
and there's no turning back.
I have much to protect now.
[OONO] And in order to
keep them all safe,
I need to become even stronger.
My vulnerability to magic
will be used against me someday
if I can't find a
way to overcome it.
[KUNAI] Tahara, I have
one more order for you.
Huh?
If anyone comes near the village
with the intent of
doing it harm, end them.
Show no mercy, understand?
I understand.
Time to go.
The old man sure is impatient.
And so am I. Let's go!
Yeah, I can't wait.
You're gonna be impossible
on this trip. Hya!
[TAHARA]
That was weird.
A memory just hit me.
Guess our conversation
must've brought it back.
What kind of memory?
It was about Chief.
The very first day I met him.
That sounds interesting.
Well, there isn't a
whole lot to it, honestly.
Just at the time,
I knew that if I hadn't
accepted the chief's invitation,
it probably would've
cost me my life.
[TAHARA]
Fact is,
I can't even hold a
candle to the guy.
[YU]
Of course you can't.
Compared to the chief, you're
little more than a paramecium.
[TAHARA] Paramecium?
That's what you're going with?
Science nerd.
[YU]
Goodbye, Chief.
I'm pining for you already.
[TAHARA]
He just left!
[YU sighs]
Prison Dungeon in
the city of Rookie.
Should be interesting.
[CITIZENS chattering]
[KUNAI]
This is the city of Rookie, huh?
Seems like a pretty
prosperous place.
[MIKAN] Let's make our way
to the Prison Dungeon,
find whatever item it
is you're looking for,
and get out of here.
Hey, old man!
Let's make prison love
in the Prison Dungeon.
Hey! They're here!
The heroes came back!
[CITIZENS gasping]
[KUNAI]
What heroes?
Uh... Huh?!
[ALL]
To be continued!