Aide Summon!
No more messing around!
Isami Tahara!
I command you to
appear before me!
Huh? Well now, if it
isn't the chief.
Wait, where the hell are we?
[OONO]
Yeah, that's Tahara all right.
[clears throat]
I'm glad you're here, Tahara.
Let's go inside.
Find a good place where
we can sit down and talk.
Oh, sure.
[TAHARA]
I don't get it.
Is this the new Infinity Game
arena or something?
Looks like they blew tons
of money, as usual, huh.
Yeah, well.
I feel like there's
something I should mention.
You're no longer
in a world where
the Great Empire is
even known to exist.
Sorry, what?
What is it, then?
Seriously, you sayin' it's
some sort of fantasy world?
Like I'm in a damn
anime or something?
Yeah, to be blunt,
it's just like that.
Huh.
[OONO]
There it is.
Tahara's head is
churning away, I can tell.
He's coming up with a whole
slew of theories and ideas
about what's going
down right now.
Well, I know there's no way
that you're pranking me.
That kinda thing just
isn't your style.
[KUNAI]
So you know, Yu is here.
Gah!
That mad woman is here?
You're kidding me, right?
I'm gonna need you to
cooperate with her.
Sorry, did you happen
to drop your left arm?
Or perhaps, maybe, your right?
Both. I lost both,
it would appear.
Well, that seems like
quite the predicament!
But, tell you what, I'll do you
a little favor just for today.
[shrieks]
Oops, that's my bad.
It looks like I unfortunately
mixed up your arms.
Are you serious?
This is not a laughing matter!
[OONO] She's a pretty
one, but damn scary.
Why'd I decide to program
her that way, anyway?
[TAHARA] Hey, Chief. You mind
if I clear something up?
Sure, what is it?
What you said before
about the Great Empire‐‐
Are you serious about it
not existing in this world?
There's no doubt in
my mind, not even one.
[sighs] Well, let me tell you,
if this truly is a world
without the Great Empire,
I really couldn't
be any happier.
One more question for you.
What exactly do you
plan to do in this place?
Sorry, but I can't say much
about it at this point.
Although,
I will admit, I'm seriously
considering heading
in the opposite direction
of the Great Empire.
Yeah?
Well, whatever.
Bottom line, if it
weren't for you,
I know Manami and I
would've died like dogs.
[OONO] Ah, yes, Manami.
The little sister
Tahara's always been so
fiercely protective of.
[MANAMI]
Big Brother!
[TAHARA]
Manami!
[MANAMI]
Big Brother!
[TAHARA]
Manami!
[MANAMI]
Big Brother!
[TAHARA]
Manami!
So do we have a plan of action
for the time being, Chief?
Well, first, we have to manage
this dirt‐poor village.
And we've got our
work cut out for us
because its only three draws are
a hospital, hot springs,
and a bath house.
You'll need to do things that'll
continue developing the area,
like job training
for the residents,
overseeing the new businesses,
managing any trouble,
negotiating with nobles,
developing a childcare program.
Uh, what else?
Are you being serious?
I'm one man. I'm not
some freakin' robot!
Yeah, but you're a damn genius.
I know you can do this.
Come on, it's me talking,
so you know it's true.
[TAHARA gasps]
Hey, you okay?
It‐‐It felt like
I'd been zapped!
What the hell's going on?
[KUNAI] You think
something's wrong with you?
Have Yu take a look.
[TAHARA]
Yeah, no thanks!
The day I let that
psycho touch me
is the day I end up in
little bitty pieces!
[YU] Come now,
that's not nice, Tahara.
Huh? Gah!
The mad woman!
Oh, I mean, hello again!
How nice to see you!
Long time no see. What a treat.
Demon Lord, who's this
new person with you?
I won't lie, he looks like
a big pervert to me.
[LUNA] Are you one of
the Demon Lord's lackeys?
Such a pretty color.
You must be very kind.
Don't know if I'd say that.
[OONO]
Now, then.
All that's left are the
preparations to welcome Madam.
[music playing]
[MANNEN] My goodness. What kind
of magical device is this?
Hey, don't get too
excited quite yet.
Look, it even has a second
key for you to wind up.
[MANNEN]
Hmm. I'm just curious.
Is this another item
of yours from overseas?
[KUNAI]
Yes, that's right.
In my country, letting this
play on cold winter nights
while sipping on some nice wine
is a common practice for
the more refined folks.
It doesn't get any
better than that, really.
Well, I must say,
it truly is a masterpiece.
It's hard to believe‐‐the fact
that it's so easy, I mean.
Who knew you could enjoy music
without even a musician?
[KUNAI] Well for balls
and high society stuff,
of course, you'd
still need those.
However, if you're
all alone in your room
or maybe hosting a small,
informal group of people,
this is much less invasive and
by far the smarter choice.
Also, it's a lot more convenient
to carry around with you.
It's not the most practical
idea to march around
with an orchestra
trailing behind you.
So, what would an item like this
be valued at back
where you're from?
[KUNAI] If you don't mind,
I'd actually prefer
if you determined the value
this time, Mr. Mannen.
Whaddya say?
[gasps]
[MANNEN]
Oh, no.
I'm not even sure
how to begin judging
the value of this truly
marvelous device!
If I price it too low,
then I may end up losing
his business altogether!
[MANNEN] In your country,
I imagine this must be
a pretty expensive
item, am I right?
Well, that depends,
because, typically,
when it comes to valuing art
and other items of this nature,
their worth can be
very subjective,
not unlike the whole "beauty
is in the eye of the beholder"
thing, you know?
[MANNEN]
Shoot! I knew it.
That means he's
testing me, right?
[MANNEN]
If I'm being perfectly honest,
when you first offered me
this item for auction,
I couldn't even begin to imagine
how much it must be worth.
I've never seen
anything quite like it!
[KUNAI] So, you're saying you
believe it has tremendous value?
[MANNEN]
Are you kidding? Of course I do!
There are plenty of people
who would be interested
in a magical item like this.
You just have to know
where to find them.
[KUNAI]
Good to know.
In that case, what's the least
you think it might sell for
if it were to go up for auction?
Just give me your best guess.
[MANNEN]
It's time! I feel it!
This is the moment when
he'll make his decision!
If I screw up now,
then I bet Mr. Kunai
will take his device to
some other store owner.
I'll lose out on
more than just this.
He'll end up taking all
of his future business
to someone else, too!
[MANNEN] If it were me,
I'd start at no less than
15 gold coins.
Someone who can't
afford that much
has no business at
an auction, anyway.
And it's a waste of time to
start any lower than that.
[KUNAI] You have a
remarkably discerning eye.
I was right to put my
faith in you, my friend.
[BINGO] Oh! Mr. Kunai!
We're so excited to have you!
Give him a Bingo
welcome, ladies!
[WOMEN]
Welcome to our shop, sir!
Thanks.
So, I'm going to need
some outfits made.
We're looking at 20 of each.
Does that sound doable?
One moment, please,
while I look.
[BINGO] Let's see,
the tuxedos on their own
shouldn't be too big of a deal,
but is he really serious
about making these
suits and tights for women?
What a tantalizing
design choice!
I mean, who does stitched
tights like this?
Seriously! No one, that's who!
Sure, we'll be able to
make these with no problem.
That's great news.
Just so you understand,
I'm going to need them done
as quickly as possible.
And as soon as you
finish them up,
it's important that they're sent
directly to Rabby Village.
I do understand wanting
them done quickly,
but I'm afraid these will
take some time to make.
[KUNAI] I'm prepared to
compensate you handsomely
for the extra rush.
[ALL gasp]
[KUNAI] And of course, this is
only the first installment.
If you complete
the work quickly,
I can even add another
two to that total.
Can you do it?
I hope the answer is yes!
'Course we can! I swear!
We'll work day and night until
every last stitch is complete.
That's very good to hear.
I'd ask that you begin
work at once, in that case.
[BINGO]
Everyone! It's time for battle!
Go on! Get started!
[WOMEN]
Right!
[WORKERS]
Thank you, Mister Demon Lord!
[OONO] Bread, milk, vegetables,
meat, and eggs. Good.
Now food will get delivered
directly to Rabby
every so often,
which is what I wanted.
The expenses
definitely added up,
but I've still got three
gold coins left over
after all of this. We should
easily be able to manage things
for a while on that much.
So, everything's more
or less ready now.
[OONO] It's funny how different
I feel about these two avatars.
Like, Kunai's the
house I grew up in,
and Zero's the room I
rented when I moved out.
Looking back,
I'm remembering how much
I used him during the
heyday of the game.
When it comes down to it,
we've been partners
for about ten years.
[OONO] What's this feeling
swelling up from deep inside?
That persistent urge to crush
the strong and help the weak.
To face my opponents
no matter who they are.
That fierce desire to be a hero
which simply won't be denied.
It's as if he's really a‐‐
No, like I'm a
dragon, after all.
[KIRISAME grunts]
Look at me. I'm a beast.
I'll bust everything in my way.
I'm the strongest one alive!
Just wait, piece of shit empire.
I'm really gonna need to figure
out how to revert at will.
[BUNNY WORKERS chattering]
[BUNNY CHILDREN gasp]
[KYON]
You guys!
Let's break for lunch now, hop!
[BUNNY WORKERS chattering]
[BUNNY CHILD 09D]
It's so good, bunny!
[BUNNY CHILD 09E]
Wanna share mine, hop?
[BUNNY CHILD 09F]
Looks tasty, hop!
Kyon! How about we
go freshen up, bunny?
Good idea. Let's do it, hop!
[BUNNY WORKERS chatter]
[BUNNY CHILD 09B] It's time
to cleanse you with water!
[BUNNY CHILD 09G]
Let's make huge...
[BUNNY CHILD 09C] I'll douse
you and make you repent!
Just kidding, hop!
I can't believe we
have such a nice place
to wash during breaks!
Seems too good to be true, hop!
I know! I don't think
I've ever been
this clean before
in my life, bunny!
[BOTH gasp, laugh]
All right, I've
taught you everything
you need to know for the job.
Now, the only thing left to do
is to put it into practice.
Let's begin.
[TAHARA]
Whoa, whoa, hold up.
Did you forget?
I said you should
sweep up the trash
before you start
brushing, remember?
Forget that and you'll end
up making a bigger mess.
Right, I'm sorry, Mr. Tahara.
[TAHARA]
It's fine. Mistakes happen.
Repeating the same mistake
is what you want to avoid.
That's lazy.
And it means you haven't
learned anything.
Always keep learning
and you'll succeed!
[BUNNY WORKERS grunting]
Oh?
So, bunny suits for a
hot spring resort, huh?
I admit, I had my doubts,
but now, it's growing on me.
Of course, it helps that
you're actually bunny people.
These are the most
embarrassing clothes ever.
Just kill me now, hop.
You guys are perverts, bunny.
I think you'll get used to it.
Try shaking your butts
if you want extra tips.
[KYON]
Are you kidding me, hop?
[MOMO]
No bunny for you, buddy.
[TAHARA] Anyway, it's time to
review how to greet customers.
[BOTH gasp]
Give them a nice, firm bow,
then hold it for three seconds.
And don't forget to smile
and speak clearly.
Thank you so much for
coming to see us, hop!
Welcome! Thank you
for joining us, bunny!
Better!
[TAHARA] Manami would look
so cute in a bunny suit.
[MANAMI] Thanks for
coming to visit, big bro!
[KUNAI] Allow me to welcome
you to Rabby, Madam.
Well, aren't you
perfect, as usual!
And, my. What a
charming little village!
It looks different than the
rumors led me to believe.
Oh, this is nothing.
We've actually only just
started on these renovations.
Give it another month or two
and I guarantee you won't even
believe your eyes, Madam!
Come back then and
you'll feel like you've
died and gone
directly up to heaven.
I have to admit, everything
you've shown me thus far
has truly lived up to your word.
[KUNAI]
It's this, right here.
Some soap?
[LUNA] Oh! That soap is
seriously the best thing, ever!
It washes away dirt like
magic and leaves your skin
so clean it sparkles!
[SHRIMPFRY]
Magic. Sparkling, huh?
[OONO]
That soap was a real hit!
[SAMBO] Oh? So, this the village
you were talking about, Madam?
[SHRIMPFRY]
Hold it right there, Gramps.
[SAMBO]
Hmm?
I told you to wait
till I called for you.
Well, you see, old folks like
me don't really like waiting.
Madam, might I ask
who this gentleman is?
If you must know,
this old fool causing nothing
but trouble is Commander Sambo.
As you can tell,
he doesn't see very well.
I only brought him along
to show him a good time
since the general
assumption is that
he doesn't have many years left.
You know, your mouth is just
as poisonous as ever, Madam.
Don't you think you should
show your elders more respect?
Speaking of mouths, hush.
I'm sorry, sir.
It sounds as if your
condition is quite serious.
But perhaps we might be able
to do something to help you.
Oh, I guess you must be the man
that Madam was talking about.
As she said,
I'm Commander Sambo,
former retainer to Head
Soldier Marshall Arts.
[OONO]
Arts? Who was that again?
Oh? The renowned
Master Arts, you mean?
This'll be fun. I can imagine
the tales of your exploits
are great and plentiful.
[SAMBO grunts]
Yes, but several years ago,
a magical beast unfortunately
took both my eyes.
I decided to go ahead and retire
because I'm not much
use to anyone anymore.
It must've been
really tough for you.
It just so happens,
one of the folks on my team
is an exceptional doctor.
I'd be surprised if she couldn't
heal your eyes altogether.
[gasps] You're not
jerking my chain, right?
If you'd like, I'll take
you to her right now.
[SAMBO] Please do! Even if
there's only a slim chance,
this is more hope than
I've felt in a long time!
Goodness, you're being
a bothersome old man.
I'm very sorry about this.
We definitely didn't mean
to make more work for you.
It's no problem in
the slightest, Madam.
Go ahead, Tahara,
you can take him inside.
[TAHARA]
This way, Master Sambo.
[SAMBO]
Thank you.
[KUNAI]
Yu.
[YU]
Yep, on it, Chief.
Hello, welcome to you both.
I'm glad to have you here.
[SHRIMPFRY]
Look at this place.
It feels like I've stumbled into
another world or something.
Go on, Gramps.
Won't you just have her
take a look already?
Would you back off,
you meddling woman?
I'm not likely to run
away from her, am I?
Then get on with it,
you senile old man!
[YU] Master Sambo, are you
ready to begin the examination?
[SAMBO] I'd like to
say I'm sorry, first,
for exposing you to
this awful thing.
It's the venom of a Scarecrow.
That's what did this to me.
[YU]
Okay.
[SAMBO] These days, I can only
see the outline of a person,
and that's on a really good day.
I can't tell you
how grateful I'd be
if you could make it any better.
Please, rest assured.
In the country I came from,
we have a medicine that
treats your symptoms
and I think you're a
perfect candidate.
[SAMBO gasps] My goodness,
you're really serious?
Yes, please wait a moment.
[KUNAI] Interesting,
she plans to cure him
simply through medicine.
Now that I think about it,
she's probably right.
It'd be a bit much to expose
them to Yu's Hand of God.
All right, please look up.
[SAMBO]
Like this?
[SAMBO gasps]
There you go.
Now, I want you to
open your eyes real slow.
[gasping]
I can see everything!
You did it! My eyes are
totally back to normal!
Gramps, are you completely sure?
Oh, Madam!
You've fattened up a bit
since the last time I saw you!
What have you been eating
to get yourself that big?
[SHRIMPFRY] Would you kindly
shut up, you walking corpse?
[SAMBO cries]
I can hardly believe it!
Thank you so much.
Now that you're healed,
you can go back to
your old post again.
I'm sure Arts would be
delighted to see you.
[SAMBO]
That's right!
Lord Arts, your loyal Sambo
is coming back to serve you!
Ah! I'm so sorry for having
caused such a big ruckus.
I'll be happy to pay for
all the damages, of course.
[YU]
This is...
It's a holy lambda coin!
Its value depends on the market,
but I've heard they're worth
a hundred giant gold
coins at the very least.
So, you're sure?
Of course, it's fine!
That stubborn old blockhead
is indebted to me
thanks to you and your medicine,
and that's worth a lot.
Truly.
So much more than any number
of holy lambda coins,
that's for certain.
Well, if you insist.
You know, I have a strong
feeling that you and I
are going to become
great friends.
What a coincidence!
I think so, too.
[BOTH chuckling]
[chuckles]
[KUNAI]
Tell me, Tahara.
How are you feeling about
not being able to see
your little sister here?
[TAHARA crying]
Manami... Manami!
[KUNAI]
Uh...
[TAHARA]
It's fine!
With us running a business
like we're in the yakuza,
it's really a lot better
that she's not around!
[OONO sighs] You're always
such a nervous Nellie
when it comes to your sister.
[AKU] Demon Lord,
what's a nervous Nellie?
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry , Episode 10.
"Madam Roars."