[LUNA]
Hey, watch it!
Be a little more careful
where you're going!
I'm terribly sorry, Miss Luna,
please forgive me!
What, do you think it's
funny or something?
Bruising my butt right before
I subdue the Demon Lord?
[COACH 2A]
Uh, begging your pardon,
but is this even a good idea
without the other Holy Maidens?
[LUNA] Excuse me,
what are you suggesting?
Are you saying it's too
much for me to handle?
[COACH 2A]
No, of course not!
You're more than
enough on your own.
[LUNA]
Hmph! Of course I am.
Can't let my sisters show me up.
Well, not forever, anyway!
Reporting in!
I've just seen the Holy
Maiden, Luna Elegant.
She's approaching this
way on the road, sir,
with an escort of 20 troops!
Really?
Does that mean she's come here
to subjugate us, at last?
[WENGOAL] What a great
honor for a Holy Maiden
to come deal with us
herself, don't you think?
I look forward to
facing her head‐on.
[SCOUT 2A] Well, actually,
unless I'm mistaken,
it doesn't seem like
her target is us Moles.
[WENGOAL]
Oh?
It's starting to get
dark pretty quickly now.
Yeah, that appears to be true.
Whaddya think,
should we camp out here?
[AKU]
Really? Right here?
[AKU gasps]
Come forth, fragment
of my intelligence!
Fulfill my need.
Survival Goods!
[AKU gasps]
There is no end to the
depth of my darkness!
Defense goods, now!
Whoa!
[KUNAI]
Believe it or not, on their own,
they don't achieve much, but...
Item Combine!
[KUNAI]
Construct Base!
Wow, that was incredible!
Did I just witness some magic?
I can't get over how
wonderful you are!
[KUNAI laughs]
You have no idea!
This baby can even withstand an
attack from a rocket launcher.
You're as good as
dead in Infinity Game
unless you camp like this.
If you don't,
it's practically suicidal.
That sounds really fascinating.
Not that I understand exactly
what you're talking about.
I'm just saying it's
pretty sturdy, that's all.
You're looking at our little
home for tonight, Aku.
I'm a pretty delicate guy,
so there's no way I'm
camping under the stars
or any crap like that.
Great! And you can leave
all the chores to me!
[AKU gasps]
Is this a...?
[KUNAI] Go on. Relax and
give that tired body a wash.
But, hold on a second!
It's just, I couldn't
possibly use this.
Sorry, I get that it's cramped,
but this is the best
I can do for right now.
No, that's not what I meant.
Just wait and see.
Someday, I'm gonna build an
entire hot spring resort,
and you'll love every
single minute of it!
How interesting. I wonder
what a "hot spring resort" is.
[OONO] Well, looks like
this world has a moon, too.
What if I gather
enough skill points
to unlock administrator
privileges?
Could that help me
return to my world?
Although,
I know that whole system is
based off of Infinity Game,
and unfortunately,
it's not like there's a
"return to my world" command.
If being summoned by that
idol is what brought me here,
then chances are
the only way to return
would be to seek out something
with a similar type of power.
[OONO sighs] Let's hope I find
a clue in the Holy Capital.
[OONO]
But even if I do go back,
would I still have the
same life from before?
Do I still have a job?
I bet my manager's pissed.
[AKU]
Demon Lord, thank you!
I washed myself with
that sapo again.
Yep. You don't smell like
garbage and sad anymore.
Oh, my gosh,
do you really mean it?
That's the first time anybody
has ever said that to me!
[KUNAI] Are you planning
to sleep right there?
[AKU]
Is that okay?
[KUNAI groans]
[KUNAI] I know you're getting
these kind of paternal vibes
from me right now,
but I'm more like
older brother material.
I'm not some old man!
[AKU]
Demon Lord?
I don't really understand, so I
think I'm gonna go to sleep.
[BANDITS chattering]
[WENGOAL] Bring it on,
Holy Maiden and friends.
We'd silence a crying baby
before we'd let you sneak past.
Nothing slips under
the Moles' noses.
[WENGOAL]
What the hell? Who're those two?
What do you want
us to do, Chief?
Well, I'm guessing they're bait.
So, the moment we attack them,
the Holy Maiden and her crew
will most likely jump
out and ambush us.
Should we do nothing
and let them go, then?
No, we'll get 'em.
A quick attack and
a quick retreat.
Draw the Holy Maiden out
into unfamiliar terrain.
[KUNAI]
These guys are such a joke,
but I'll go ahead and
turn off my intercept
and auto‐attack
abilities just in case.
[KUNAI]
Aku, stand back.
[AKU]
Huh?
[KUNAI] I guess I should
just take this attack.
Hmph, really, though?
Under level 30?
Do you even grind?
[OONO] In Infinity Game, only
players at the max level of 30
were able to inflict any
sort of damage to Kunai,
so if that holds true here,
this guy's no threat.
[KUNAI] How about if we
just skip the hide‐and‐seek
and you show yourself?
[BANDITS cackling]
[WENGOAL]
Hey there, tough guy.
I'm Chief of the Moles.
Call me O Wengoal!
And you are?
That's my manager!
What in the world
is he doing here?
Sorry I've been out.
I seem to've gotten
isekai‐ed somehow.
What are you talking about?
Okay. What the hell.
I swear it's him.
[WENGOAL]
Quit mumbling to yourself.
Uh, just checking.
You aren't my manager, Aoki?
Hah. I see.
You're trying to confuse
me now, aren't you?
'Cause that's a
waste of your time.
No, that wasn't
my intention, but...
[OONO] I mean, am I going insane
or do they look exactly alike?
Considering that trick
you just conjured up,
I'm taking it you're
a magic user?
[KUNAI] I've got no
obligation to answer that.
Try to ignore us
and you'll get hurt.
Got it, geezer bait?
Who're you calling geezer?
Seriously, you're older than me!
Are you kidding me?
If anyone here is
sporting an old stank face,
it's definitely you!
[WENGOAL, KUNAI yelling]
[AKU] Mister Demon Lord,
let's get out of here!
Did she call you a Demon Lord?
A diaper baby like you?
Go pretend you're a Demon
Lord in the afterlife!
[BANDIT 2B groans]
[BANDITS gasp]
I was right! I knew he
had to be a magic user!
[LUNA]
What was that about magic?
[WENGOAL gasps]
[BANDITS yell]
[KUNAI]
'Kay, what the?
[LUNA] Who would've thought
I'd go Demon Lord hunting
and end up with a bunch a
filthy bandits in the bargain?
Crap, everything's ruined.
Pull back, men! Retreat!
[LUNA]
How stupid can you be?
Do you actually think
you can get away from me?
Be torn asunder by gold!
Gold Slash!
[BANDITS yelling]
[WENGOAL]
This girl is a nightmare!
[gasps]
[KUNAI groans]
[KUNAI]
Ow, ow.
My Assault Barrier
never activated.
So, this kid is max level?
To be honest, I wasn't
expecting very much out of you.
What did you just say?
That was awfully rude!
[KUNAI] Anyway, do I not
at least get an apology
for being attacked
without any provocation?
[LUNA] Hmph! A Holy
Maiden dispatching evil
is just plain common sense,
you should know that.
All right, then.
I'm fine with those
being your last words.
Aww. Seems to me as if you
don't have any idea who I am.
I'm one of the
three Holy Maidens.
The Golden Luna Elegant.
[KUNAI]
Your name's "Elegant"
and you go around shooting off
magic like some kinda maniac?
Way to not live up
to the name, squirt.
Get him, now!
I want you to capture
this blockhead!
[KNIGHTS]
Yes ma'am!
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[KUNAI] Unfortunately, gents,
not a single one of you
has any business
standing in front of me.
[KNIGHT 2A yells]
[LUNA gasps]
[LUNA]
Who in the world is this guy?
Hey, stop there! Just what
do you think you're doing?
[gasps]
[KUNAI groans] I don't hold
back on those who attack me,
even if they do
happen to be women.
Huh? Wait, hold on,
what's happening?
What're you doing?
[KUNAI grunts]
That hurt!
[LUNA gasps]
No, for real!
[LUNA whines]
Ow, my butt! You're
hurting my poor butt!
That one would be
for attacking me!
And this is for
underestimating me!
Let's see, what else
can I think of?
No, you have to stop!
[KUNAI]
And this one
is frankly because
I'm really enjoying this.
[LUNA]
Ow!
[KUNAI sighs]
Well, that was a good workout.
I kinda wonder about the
Holy Maiden's butt, though.
Do you think it'll be okay?
I'm pretty sure it's already got
a split in it. She'll be fine.
Right, that's not quite
what I meant, though.
[KUNAI] Now then. Since we've
got all this money to blow,
what would you say to
a stay in the city?
[LUNA groans] I'm totally
going to kill that guy!
You just wait and
see if I don't!
You idiot coachman!
Didn't I already tell you
to go a whole lot slower
because this stings my butt?
Really.
Whoever named things
in this kingdom
needs a kick right in the scrod.
You think so?
[KUNAI] Come on, let's buy
a bunch of random stuff
with all this money.
[AKU] But that money belongs to
the Holy Maiden, doesn't it?
[KUNAI] Hey, I was
acting in self‐defense.
In fact, it could be argued
that I was actually
being kind and lenient.
If this were an eroge,
we'd be heading for
a sex slave route.
[AKU] Mister Demon Lord,
what's eroge?
[KUNAI sniffs]
[KUNAI]
How much?
[VENDOR 2A] It'll be three
coppers for two skewers.
[VENDOR 2A]
Thank you. Come again!
Um, what's this?
Look, it's my treat today.
Just eat it and enjoy, okay?
I've never eaten anything
this delicious before!
[KUNAI chuckles]
[KUNAI] This place is just one
terrible name after another.
[AKU]
You think so?
I've always kinda thought
this was a cute name.
[GUGULE WORKER 2A]
Welcome.
[KUNAI] I'd like the
best room you've got.
If you'd like to stay
in our premiere room,
that would cost one gold coin.
Oh, no, we shouldn't spend
that much, Mister Demon Lord!
Uh, Demon Lord?
My name's De Mon, so it's
kinda turned into a joke.
Sorry to freak you
out like that!
[KUNAI]
Now, if you please.
Right. Of course,
very good, sir.
I'll go prepare the room.
[KUNAI] You can't call me
"Demon Lord" in front of people!
Refer to me as your older
brother or something!
[AKU] Well, what about
if I call you "Papa"?
[KUNAI] I'm still a young,
swingin' single dude!
[AKU gasps]
[GUGULE WORKER 2A]
Please, make yourselves at home.
I hope you enjoy your stay.
[KUNAI] Hmm. Not a bad view,
if I do say so myself.
[OONO]
If I'm honest,
I'm surprised at how luxurious
this place actually is.
But, of course, I can't let on
'cause I've got to keep
my cool around Aku.
[AKU]
Gorgeous!
It's almost like we're
staying at a noble's estate!
Well you're easily
impressed, aren't you?
This is nothing compared
to the castle I'll build
befitting my greatness one day.
A castle, huh?
I mean, I'm not sure
what you're talking about,
but it sounds great!
Now then, I'm thinking
we should definitely
treat ourselves to a
nice dinner tonight.
But, uh, one order
of business first.
[BINGO] Dear me, that's one
shabby outfit. Poor thing.
I wonder if she's his
servant or something?
Welcome to you both!
Is there anything in particular
that you're looking for?
Thanks, yeah,
we could use a little help
finding this one a new
outfit that suits her.
I'm not really the best at
picking out clothes for people.
I'd rather leave
that to the pros.
Okay, hold on, this one
looks like the biggest.
I'm gonna use this guy.
[BINGO]
What?
No, Demon Lo‐‐
Just so we're clear,
you're planning to spend that
giant gold coin in
our establishment?
[KUNAI]
Is it not enough?
Ha, ha! Don't be silly!
We're at your service!
I'll go put something together
for you immediately!
Hello, miss! Right this way.
Oh, okay.
I'd like to smoke, but I'm
not seeing any ash trays.
Use my hands!
It would be an honor for you to
dispose of your ash on my body!
Oh, uh, no, that
won't be necessary!
All I need is an ash tray
and a place to sit down, so‐‐
Use me!
Please, sir, it'd be my pleasure
for you to sit on my back!
[OONO] What the hell?
This place is a little scary.
[AKU]
I'm sorry to make you wait.
I don't know.
Do you think this outfit
looks okay on me?
[OONO] Ooh! I figured she'd
shine up with a bit of polish,
but this is such a
big transformation!
Uh. Yeah.
[OONO] Whoa! Since when did Aku
have different colored eyes?
How did I miss that?
Maybe I shouldn't
mention it, though.
‐‐[rustling]
‐‐[KUNAI] Hm?
If you'd like, I can also
bring you several other
options to look over.
Just say the word,
and it's done.
[KUNAI]
Let's see.
Yes, I'll take everything
that suits her.
I'm sorry, sir, but did you
really just say "everything"?
Yeah, I'll buy it all.
Ladies, quick! Bring me the best
of everything we have
in the young miss's size!
[LADY 2A] I wonder if they're
father and daughter.
[LADY 2B] I don't really get
that vibe, though, do you?
[GENTLEMAN 2A]
I think he must own some land
around here or something.
[GENTLEMAN 2B]
I heard he paid for her outfit
with a giant gold coin
without batting an eye.
[CUSTOMERS whispering]
[GENTLEMAN 2A]
Ooh! See that?
He chose a wine only a true
connoisseur would order!
[GENTLEMAN 2B] Seems like
he's a man of good taste.
It seriously feels
like I'm dreaming.
[KUNAI]
Hm?
[AKU]
I just can't thank you enough
for doing all of this
for someone like me.
Don't worry about it.
Let's just eat before
it gets cold, okay?
[AKU]
I do worry about it!
It's weird. Why are you
being so nice to me?
[OONO]
I mean, that's a fair question.
I wonder what makes
me go so far for her.
Would you please tell
me if there's any way
to repay you for your
great kindness to me?
Anything that you want!
If it's something I can do,
then I'll do it for you!
Did you really just offer
to do anything I want?
‐‐[AKU gasps]
‐‐[KUNAI] Hm?
Now I've got you, Demon Lord!
[GENTLEMAN 2A]
"Demon Lord"?
[LADY 2A] I wonder if she's
talking about that man!
You dare to sit here
and eat with my money?
Are you stupid?
Do you wanna die?
[KUNAI]
I think you're forgetting.
That money's mine now.
You offered it to
me as an apology.
'Cause if I hadn't done that,
you wouldn't have stopped with
the endless spanking of my butt!
Okay, no need to mess yourself.
Why don't you sit
down and join us?
We wouldn't want to disturb the
other guests, now, would we?
Give me one good reason why I
should listen to you! [gasps]
[KUNAI] Well, do you want
to be disciplined again?
[gasps]
[KUNAI] Glad to see you
know how to be reasonable.
Everyone, I'd like to apologize
for causing that commotion.
If you'd allow me,
I'd like to make
it up to you all
by treating each table
to a bottle of wine,
with my compliments.
Oh, my, that's so generous!
Yeah, he seems like a
really upstanding guy.
Garson, something nice
for the little lady.
[KUNAI] It's my treat,
so have as much as you'd like.
You jerk! More like
it's my treat, right?
Um. I'm so sorry, Holy Maiden.
But the Demon Lord isn't
actually a bad person, you know.
What's wrong with you?
There's no such thing
as a good Demon Lord!
[AKU]
Huh?
I guess it's true.
You can be so kind sometimes,
but you can also be mean.
I always act like a
perfect gentleman.
It's just that I'm picky
about who I treat nicely.
Oh, dear.
The Holy Maiden is actually
a very important
person, Demon Lord.
[AKU gasps]
[OONO]
Well,
I guess I can't carry her on
my back with a dress on, so.
[AKU] Okay, I've changed
my mind. You're mostly kind.
[KUNAI]
Hm?
[knocking]
Idiot! Now I've got no
money to stay anywhere,
and it's all thanks to you!
[KUNAI] What's the problem?
Can't you just camp somewhere?
Whatever happened to your
troupe, sad little Luna?
I sent them home,
thank you very much!
[KUNAI]
Really? Why would you do that?
[LUNA]
Why do you think? Because...
I didn't want to put them in any
more danger for no good reason!
So you thought it might be a
good time for us to hang out?
No! That's not what
I'm saying at all!
[AKU]
Demon Lord!
Sorry, but could you please
be a little bit nicer
to the Holy Maiden?
[KUNAI]
All right, then. Here.
What is it?
Is there something
else that you want?
O‐Okay, fine, so be it.
I'll let the two of you
stay in this room with me.
[KUNAI] You sure your
head's on straight?
[LUNA] Well, you reserved the
room with my money, didn't you?
I'd say it's only proper that
I'm allowed to sleep in it!
Oh, wow, I think she might
have you there, Demon Lord!
[KUNAI groans]
[BANDITS yelling]
Sister! We've almost
reached the city!
[KILLER QUEEN]
How dare that shitty brat.
She's gonna regret
causing me trouble.
[OONO] Okay, favorite
old‐school games. I'll start!
Shenmue's definitely
gotta be on the list.
An open world in a time
like that was just amazing.
With motion capture and fully‐
voiced NPCs in the city, too.
Not to mention having
a full game cycle
of morning, noon, and night.
That was so sick!
It's making me wanna
play again. Loved it!
[AKU] Demon Lord. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 3.
"Killer Queen."