[LUNA] So. You said your name
was Aku, isn't that right?
[gasps]
Well, from now on, I want
you to call me Sister Luna.
Is it okay for me to be so
informal with a Holy Maiden?
I say it's fine,
therefore, it's fine.
I make the rules here.
Right.
[LUNA] Besides, we're already
comfy enough together
to see each other
naked! [giggles]
Here I come!
[AKU] Whoa! What're
you doing down there?
Administrator privileges.
Item file.
[OONO]
I'm so used to Infinity Game,
where players couldn't hold any
more than ten items at a time.
Getting to store
infinite items like this
makes things a lot easier.
[KUNAI]
Luna, got a minute?
Sorry, you say something?
Are we on a first
name basis now?
Fine. Whatever.
I just need you to tell me
everything you know
about the Cherub.
Um, pardon me, Sister Luna.
It's just that Demon Lord isn't
very knowledgeable
about this stuff.
Do you think you could tell
him what he needs to know?
The Cherub is dead.
It died after sealing
the Demon King, Greyole.
Doing that used up
all its power.
Well, you don't say.
[LUNA]
Thankfully for us,
the Kingdom of Holy Light still
has the Ophan and the Seraph,
and they serve as
guides to the people.
To think the peace
of the kingdom
could actually be threatened.
That's truly absurd.
[SOLDIERS hollering]
Sister!
We've almost reached
the city of Yahoo!
Good. I'm ready to tie a rope
around that friggin' brat's neck
and drag her home.
I gotta say, it's gutsy of her
to try to subdue a Demon Lord.
We're all pretty impressed with
your sister's fierce bravery
and her utter fearlessness!
You're all morons.
That little twerp's just
doing it for attention.
As if a Demon Lord exists,
anyway, the idiot.
But lots of people
are saying that
Greole really was
killed by someone!
Hmph, you're such a meat‐head.
How dare my big sister withhold
information from me like that!
[KILLER QUEEN] Did you really
think you could ever beat me,
you maggot?
[KUNAI] I've got a grasp
on the Cherub situation.
So?
Do you care to tell me where I
can find the Ophan and Seraph?
Dunno. It's been ages
since anyone in the kingdom
has seen either of them.
[KUNAI]
Oh, it's only a legend, then.
There are some
misguided believers
who have convinced themselves
that the stone statue
at the Wishing Shrine
is actually the Ophan.
But it's fine. They'll
get divine retribution
for that someday.
[KUNAI]
Could it be possible
that the Idol
actually was the Ophan?
[IDOL] I was once a
beautiful sight to behold.
A symbol of purity, but many
years of granting wicked wishes
to humans turned me into this.
[KUNAI] Still don't
have enough information
to form a proper plan just yet.
I've gotta gather more
intel in the Holy Capital.
But before I can do that,
I guess I'd better do something
about this empty wallet of mine.
[KUNAI] In my motherland,
we've traditionally had
a strong appreciation
for taste and elegance.
So, everyone always
presents their finest wares
when serving tea.
In fact, you're considered
an embarrassment to your family
if you dare to put out
something that looks cheap.
Well, goodness, that
certainly is interesting.
[KUNAI] So, today. I've brought
my very favorite tea bowl
from my motherland with me.
It's incredible!
Look how splendid it is!
[OONO] Right, as in this
trash I literally just made
with a few skill points and
that only gives one offense?
I just don't get it.
So, tell me, how much would it
cost for you to part with it?
No, no, no.
I'd like for you to think of
this as a small token given
only in hopes of establishing
a long‐lasting partnership.
However, seeing as how I don't
have very much money on hand,
I'd be happy to accept
one giant gold coin
as collateral if you're willing.
Um, one giant gold coin?
[OONO] That looked like
the most expensive coin
in Luna's bag by far, so.
I figured I should
probably start with that,
but who knows, I guess?
[MANNEN] I've heard all those
incredible rumors about you,
you know.
They whisper that
you're a cultured guy,
even descended from royalty,
as well as a very tolerant,
accepting gentleman.
[KUNAI laughs]
Who would dare go around
spreading baseless
rumors like that?
Look, I'm sure you must have
your own reasons for denying it,
but I can promise you, I won't
tell anyone else about it.
So no need to worry.
I'll gladly accept
your proposition.
Let me go get things
ready for you.
[KUNAI]
I appreciate your understanding.
But before that,
I think it's important
that I tell you something.
If you end up
selling the tea bowl,
you need to be sure to
take nothing less than
five giant gold coins in
exchange for it. You got that?
Whoa! Five giant coins?
Are you positive?
[KUNAI]
If you can't promise me that,
then let's just pretend like
this conversation
never happened.
[MANNEN]
No, wait, please! I understand.
I promise to honor your wishes.
[OONO] Holy crap,
that sold for a ton more
than I thought it would!
The value of stuff
here is way different
than in Infinity Game!
Cool.
I'll invite Aku and Luna
to dinner or something.
[KILLER QUEEN]
Luna! Get out here!
[KUNAI]
Hm?
[WALKING] As you know,
much to our disappointment,
we demon‐believing Satanists
failed in summoning
the Demon Lord.
But if it resulted in the
Holy Maidens mobilizing
and taking action, then I say
it was not done in vain.
We will eradicate the Holy
Maidens from this world
just as we had
originally planned.
[SATANISTS] May disaster
befall the Holy Maidens.
May it befall every one of them.
[CROWD whispering]
[KILLER QUEEN]
The second eldest Holy Maiden,
Killer Queen, has come!
Luna! Get out here!
[KUNAI] Great, this one's
gonna be a handful.
She's got those crazy eyes.
While we're at it,
if there's a Demon Lord,
get your ass out here, too!
[KUNAI]
Yeah right, are you kidding?
Go back to your post‐
apocalyptic nightmare!
[LUNA]
Get out of my way!
Move it, what's wrong with you?
[LUNA gasps] Hey, Sister!
What're you doing here?
Hey, you little brat!
How dare you run off to pick a
fight without telling anyone!
Well, I heard a
Demon Lord appeared
so I thought someone should...
[KILLER QUEEN]
You imbecile!
What the hell could
you do on your own?
Next time, instead of chasing
a Demon Lord who doesn't exist,
try taking a nap,
li'l baby crap!
No, Sister, you don't
get what's going on!
There really is a Demon Lord and
I used my charms to tame him!
[KILLER QUEEN]
Oh? How cute.
And what happened next?
Or did you wake up?
[LUNA]
He exists! Also,
he's completely
obsessed with my butt!
[KILLER QUEEN]
Huh? Your butt?
[KUNAI groans]
[OONO] I mean, I get
what she's talking about,
but man does it sound super bad
when she says it like that.
[KUNAI gasps]
[SATANIST 3A]
Death to the phony angel.
Behold, my Firebird!
[SATANIST 3B] May grief
befall the Holy Maidens.
Ice hammer!
[LUNA gasps]
No!
Fuji!
[MOUNT FUJI]
I'm on it!
[KILLER QUEEN grunts]
[CROWD gasping]
[KUNAI] Why do these
outfits look so familiar?
[KUNAI]
Wait a minute.
The guys who were killed at the
Wishing Shrine wore that, too.
My, my, what a pleasure,
you Satanist scum!
[grunting]
[SATANISTS gasp]
Idiots should all just die!
‐‐[LUNA] Gold Splash!
‐‐[SATANISTS groan]
Time to wipe out
those damn Satanists!
Blood sacrifice for Sister!
Once this fight is over,
I'm gonna get Sister
to knock me around!
I mean, would you look at her?
Ha, ha, ha! Take this,
Satanist rabble!
Tell me, how does it feel
to be stained in crimson?
[KILLER QUEEN cackles]
[LUNA]
Let's be real, okay?
You should be honored to die
at the hands of my magic,
agents of evil!
[KUNAI]
You're the ones that're evil,
no matter which way
you look at it!
[KUNAI]
Hm?
This is all of my
most prized darkness.
If I give it up in exchange for
two Holy Maidens, so be it!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
What the hell?
What is this?
Luna, get back! Hades is here!
[BOTH groan]
[LUNA groans]
[KILLER QUEEN groans]
[WALKING] You fools.
Your divine protection is gone.
Shoot the Holy Maidens!
[LUNA gasps]
[MOUNT FUJI pants, groans]
[MOUNT FUJI grunting]
[KUNAI]
Yeah, okay, this is looking bad.
[RING]
Why do you hesitate?
Why not toss a grenade
over that way?
So simple.
Then you could kill
everyone at one time.
Are you insane?
What's wrong with you?
If I were to kill
the Holy Maidens,
you know all that would do
is get my face bumped up
higher on the wanted list.
[RING]
And what of it?
After all, that woman is
already after the Demon Lord.
Her along with everyone
else in this kingdom.
[KUNAI groans]
[RING]
Yes, that helps.
Now it's a clear‐cut case
of legitimate self‐defense,
just the way you like it.
You should be grateful.
[KUNAI] Damn. My body's not
moving the way I need it to!
[KUNAI]
There has to be an answer.
Don't I have anything to
help me get out of this?
[KUNAI gasps]
What?
[KUNAI] At this point, I haven't
really got much choice!
[KUNAI gasps]
[SATANISTS gasping]
[BOTH groaning]
[KILLER QUEEN gasps]
[SATANISTS murmur]
So. Where am I?
[SATANISTS gasp]
[WALKING gasps]
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
[BOTH groaning]
Tsk. How pathetic
are you guys, anyway?
Messing with women and kids?
That bastard!
Must be a Holy Maiden goon!
Not for long. Get him!
[SATANISTS yell]
Ha! You guys really
want piece of me?
[SATANISTS yelling]
[grunts]
Hya!
[SATANISTS groaning]
[gasps]
A bunch of one‐punch
weaklings. Disappointing.
[KILLER QUEEN]
Wait, who the hell is that?
And what's going on with
that smokin' white outfit?
It's so sick!
[growls] All right, who are you?
And what do you want?
[KIRISAME] Considering you're
just a gang of cowards
who harass women,
I don't think you
deserve to know my name.
[KILLER QUEEN]
A... woman?
He just called me a woman!
Huh, surprisingly,
it didn't feel half bad.
Look, he's probably just
one of the Holy Knights!
Don't worry. He‐‐[gasps]
[WALKING gasps]
[WALKING groans]
So quick!
How is he that fast?
That whole thing was
basically a blur!
Hey! You see that, Luna?
[LUNA groaning]
Ugh, you're worthless,
you know that?
'Fraid it's time to go, punks.
[KIRISAME grunting]
[SATANISTS groaning]
[KIRISAME]
Yes, dance for me!
[SATANISTS groaning]
[SATANISTS gasping, yelling]
Give it up.
No one can flee from the dragon!
[KIRISAME grunts]
[grunts]
[KIRISAME yells]
[roars]
[SATANISTS gasping]
[SATANISTS screaming]
You gutless worms are too
early to face the dragon,
by around a thousand years.
[KILLER QUEEN] He's so flippin'
cool I can barely handle it.
This is crazy!
This city doesn't seem
to be one I remember.
How're you doin'? Okay?
[KILLER QUEEN]
Uh, yeah!
[KIRISAME]
You're damn reckless, you know.
What made you decide to go up
against guys with weapons?
[KILLER QUEEN] Is this dude
actually concerned for me?
How long has it been
since that's happened?
Well, if that trash
messes with you again,
you just let me know.
I'll happily come
running to the rescue.
[KILLER QUEEN squeals]
My heart can't take it!
He's killing me right now!
I'm dead four times over!
For some reason, I can't seem to
act like myself around this guy!
What's up with that?
Argh!
I'll die if anyone sees me
like this, I seriously will!
[KILLER QUEEN]
Um, sorry to have to ask,
but would you be so kind as to
tell me your name, please?
I'll strangle you later.
I'm gonna squeeze
the life outta you.
Sure. I'm Zero.
Zero Kirisame.
Zero?
Okay, well, I'm sorry.
For dragging you into
all this, I mean.
[KIRISAME chuckles]
[KIRISAME] Hey, there's no need
for you to look so pitiful.
I mean, I'm pretty much the
definition of unrivaled,
you know?
Insignificant little
street brawl like this
barely even registers for me.
[KILLER QUEEN]
Crap! My nose is gonna bleed!
[KIRISAME] Looks like
a few people got hurt.
Go and take care of them.
I'm gonna get out of here.
[KILLER QUEEN]
Oh, okay!
Zero Kirisame.
I've finally found him.
The man of my destiny!
[WALKING panting]
You monster.
At least I was fortunate
enough to have recovered Hades.
Those with dragon blood,
who have taken up
arms against evil
and look on the ground with such
disdain, the filthy Dragonkin.
Could it even be possible
that they've formed
a kind of secret union with
the Kingdom of Holy Light?
[KUNAI grumbling]
[AKU]
Demon Lord!
It's kind of a good thing
I ran into you here!
[KUNAI] Dammit!
Will someone please kill me?
Just kill me, now!
The very definition
of unrivaled, my ass!
You're a frickin' imbecile
and I hate your guts!
Ugh! C'mere, wall!
Um, is there something
I can do, Demon Lord?
Huh? What? No!
This. Sorry. Anyway.
Aku. Did you happen
to see that guy?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
C'mon, yeah, you do.
That man who was wearing
the almost disturbingly
white clothing.
Oh! You're talking
about the Dragonkin.
I was in the hotel, so I
actually didn't get to see it,
but Sister Luna
told me about him.
When he thrust his fist,
she said it sent out a shockwave
that looks like a dragon,
and that it sent all
the bad guys flying off!
Argh, what've I done?
I hate this.
I wanna crawl inside myself
and die a thousand times.
Hope it's okay to ask,
but why is it you're
so curious about him?
Is it possible he could
be someone you know?
Hell no! I don't know that guy!
Oh, okay, I was just wondering.
[OONO]
I can't do it.
I cannot admit to her
that that guy and me
are actually one and the same!
Zero Kirisame.
Why the hell did I ever create
that hard‐ass, delinquent,
joke of a character?
What was I thinking?!
[MIKAN]
Come on, Yukikaze.
You've gotta stop wasting money
now that we're short again.
[YUKIKAZE]
Do you want a lick, Mikan?
No thank you.
And, hey, don't talk
and eat. It's so gross.
[YUKIKAZE]
Okay.
[sighs]
Look, quit being dumb and let's
just get on with this, okay?
I'm ready to go whenever.
[MIKAN]
Look at this one:
"Seeking able adventurers
to exterminate dangerous
sandwolves." Nice.
That reward isn't
too bad, either.
All right. Sounds like
a job for us, then.
Hey, excuse me!
We'd like to go ahead and
take on that one request
with the sandwolves.
[GUILD MAN 3A]
Got it. Just gimme a minute.
Ooh, check this guy out!
Hey, what about this guy?
Is he a new bounty?
Do you know what he's
s'posed to have done?
[GUILD MAN 3A] I guess he's
claiming to be the Demon Lord.
Interesting.
Wait, is his thing
a Demon Lord, too?
[MIKAN] What in the
hell are you thinking?
[KUNAI] Luna, what happened
to those soldiers?
[LUNA]
Huh? I sent them all home.
Why'd you do that?
What do you plan to do
if something happens?
Oh, well, I've got you, don't I?
Huh?
Since when and in what universe
did I become your bodyguard?
Shut your mouth!
I know you're actually
happy to be with me anyway.
Friggin' pervert.
[KUNAI] Oh, you're calling
me a pervert now? Seriously?
When have I ever done a
single perverted thing to you?
[LUNA] Be real. I know
you haven't been able to
forget the way my
butt feels, have you?
You're a total butt fetish perv!
[AKU giggles]
This is great!
I've had a really hard life.
It's just,
I've always wanted
to go on an adventure!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Right? We're glad
to have you, too!
Just be ready to work hard
and do everything I say!
Ugh, the agony.
‐‐[LUNA laughing]
‐‐[AKU giggling]
[OONO]
The other side of speed.
I'll pound you into mincemeat!
Dancing mad!
Bring me the ball!
First attacker!
The Phantom sixth
speed! [cackles]
Screw you, dumb old me!
[AKU] Demon lord,
what is it? What's wrong?
[OONO] I may have danced with
some hard luck, that's all.
[AKU] I'm sorry, but I have no
idea what you're trying to say.
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 4.
"Yu Kirino."