[OONO] Can't believe I kept
this running for 15 years.
Not bad since it
was just a hobby.
But once the clock
strikes midnight,
I'm shutting the
server down for good.
Thanks for sticking with
me till the end, everyone.
And thank you, Mister Demon
Lord of the Great Empire.
I've certainly enjoyed spreading
bloodshed and chaos
with you over the years.
Goodbye, Kunai.
Sleep well, old friend.
[SERAPH] This is a
world abandoned by God.
A world where angels
drown in despair.
But do not let fear seize you.
You must listen very carefully.
Focus and you shall
surely hear it.
The midnight bell tolls.
It signals a new beginning,
the genesis of a new "you."
[KUNAI]
Holy‐‐
What just happened?
[KUNAI groans]
Huh?
[KUNAI] Where the hell did
all this nature come from?
[KUNAI]
I wasn't wearing those shoes.
And I know damn well I wasn't
sitting in front of the computer
dressed like a
frickin' mob boss!
Whatever's goin' on here,
it can't be good.
[gasps]
The Demon Lord, Hakuto Kunai.
This must be Infinity Game!
Who did this to me? [grunts]
Even if he's the Demon Lord,
I don't wanna be some old dude!
Wait, calm down.
There's gotta be an explanation.
'Cause there's no way in hell
I got teleported inside my
own damned computer game!
On the other hand, if it is
my game, the solution's easy.
[KUNAI]
Administrator!
Okay, now we're talkin'!
Put in my password
and that'll do it.
[KUNAI]
Huh?
So am I stuck in
a different game?
Kinda starting to wish I'd
watched more isekai anime,
so I'd have a clue what
the hell was going on.
[AKU panting]
[KUNAI]
Hm? Is someone there?
[AKU panting]
[OONO]
So I'm Kunai, right?
If I'm playing the part,
I gotta be a smug jerk.
[KUNAI]
Uh, what's up, peewee?
Oh, wait, do you even
speak my language?
You have to run!
[KUNAI]
Huh?
[KUNAI] I don't suppose
this big, angry fella
is a pet of yours, is he?
'Cause, uh, now might be a nice
time to ask him to roll over.
It's dangerous!
Get away, hurry!
[GREOLE growls]
Feeble human!
I shall feast on
your miserable flesh!
Scary!
[growls]
[KUNAI grunts]
[roars]
Listen. You better
check yourself.
[GREOLE gasps]
[KUNAI grunts]
[GREOLE screams]
[OONO] I know this game
like the back of my hand
and I've never
seen one of those.
I think I'd remember
making a monster like that.
Same goes for that girl.
[gasping]
Demon Lord, please,
don't eat me!
I taste just awful, I promise!
Are you stupid?
The hell do you
take me for, kid?
[OONO gasps]
We do speak the same language.
Don't crap your pants.
No matter how hungry I get,
I'd never eat someone like you.
[gasps] Really? That's a relief.
[KUNAI] Where'd you get that
idea in the first place?
We've known each
other five minutes
and you're calling
me the "Demon Lord"?
Well, I mean,
you blew away Greole
without even breaking a sweat.
So, if you're not an angel,
what else could you be
but the Demon Lord, right?
My name is Kunai.
No "Demon Lord" or anything
else like that, okay?
[AKU]
Oh. I see.
Anyway. You got a name?
Sorry. My name's Aku.
[KUNAI, OONO chuckle]
[OONO]
"Aku?" Like "Evil"?
[KUNAI] Uh, well, that
has a lovely ring to it.
So, Aku, quick question.
We're not in Japan
right now, are we?
No. We're not.
I've never heard that word.
[KUNAI]
Hm...
[AKU] This land is known as
the Kingdom of Holy Light.
The people here
worship the Cherub.
[KUNAI]
The Cherub, huh? Tell me more.
[AKU] Well, it was the great
Cherub who sealed away Greole,
that monster you beat with
those knives of yours.
Beneath the Cherub are
the Three Holy Maidens,
then it's the Holy Knights,
and a big organization
called the Holy Church.
[KUNAI, OONO groan]
[OONO] Wow, this is just
generic fantasy land,
right down to the names, huh?
But if this isn't my
world like I thought,
then why did I
get summoned here?
I'm nobody important.
[OONO gasps]
[OONO] What if someone was
trying to summon Kunai
and I got wrapped up in it?
I guess that makes
sense? Kind of?
[KUNAI] You wanna a take
a bath? You're a mess.
[gasps] Is it really okay?
[KUNAI]
Why wouldn't it be?
I'll go wait over there and
you can jump in the lake
and scrub all of that
muck off you. Sound good?
That sounds wonderful!
Take your time. Just yell
at me when you're done.
Okay!
I didn't know the Forest of
Wishes had such a nice lake.
It's so clear and pretty!
I've never bathed in
such clean water before!
It's amazing!
[AKU]
I'm so happy I'm still alive!
That aside,
I can't help but
wonder who that man is.
[AKU gasps] Wait! What if he
only asked me to clean myself
so I'm better to eat?
Got administrator
privileges! Yeah!
[AKU]
Administrator?
Now, Item File.
[AKU gasps]
Whoa, what's that?
[AKU] He's not getting out
his cooking utensils, is he?
Here's a bath towel for you.
You can clean
yourself with this.
[gasps]
Oh, wow, is this that
stuff they call "sapo"?
Who's "they"? Ancient Romans?
[AKU]
Romans? Are they from Japan?
Just forget it.
I'm gonna take a walk.
Scout the area for monsters.
[OONO] I'm gonna run out of
skill points at this rate.
Seems to work like
Infinity Game,
where I learn skills and
get back my skill points
after winning fights.
Summoning a bar of soap and a
towel cost me five points,
so I've only got about 30 left.
I need to come up with some
kind of strategy to get more,
or this is going to be a pain.
In Infinity Game,
you get the most points for
beating higher‐level enemies,
but I don't know what that
would be in this world
or where to find it.
[AKU]
Mister Demon Lord?
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you. The sapo was great!
Enough with the "Demon Lord"
crap already. [groans]
So, that monster.
Are there a lot of them
lurking around here?
No, of course not!
One Greole is already too many.
The whole kingdom would be
wiped out if there were more!
What? You mean that
stupid‐looking thing
was actually dangerous?
Uh‐huh, uh‐huh!
[KUNAI sighs] Aku, do you know
where that thing's den is,
or maybe where it sleeps?
I could use some more
Skill Points and‐‐
[KUNAI clears throat]
I mean, there's
something I wanna see.
[AKU] I don't know
if this helps or not,
but I heard Greole
used to be sealed
at the Wishing Shrine
in this forest.
A Wishing Shrine, huh?
Since I'm new to the area,
y'think you could
guide me there?
[AKU]
Y‐Yeah, of course.
Tell me where to go and
I'll carry you on my back.
There's no need for that!
I'm filthy and disgusting.
You don't want someone
like me touching you!
Sorry, but I'm not gonna
sit here and argue with you.
Hurry up. Time to go.
[sobs]
[OONO]
Oh, come on, now you're crying?
You can't even humor me?
That hurts!
I've always been a burden.
My village would be
better without me.
That's why they have me
gather up all the garbage
from people's houses,
and throw out all
the human waste.
I've done the best I can, but...
Those are important jobs.
If you didn't do it, then the
villagers would get sick.
You shouldn't be ashamed at all.
But they...
They're always telling me
I'm filthy and disgusting.
And then they cast me out
as a sacrifice to Greole.
[AKU sobs]
[AKU]
Maybe it's better that way.
They all said they'd get
dirty if they touched me.
So you shouldn't‐‐
[AKU gasps]
[AKU] Wait! Weren't you
listening? You can't!
What the hell does it matter
if you get a little
dirty sometimes?
As long as you keep
your heart clean,
all you gotta do is take a bath
and you'll be as good as new.
Thank you, Mister Demon Lord.
You're so nice.
[KUNAI] Don't you think
you're holding on bit tight?
[AKU]
Oh. I might be.
But this is the first time I've
ever been so close to someone,
so it could take a
little getting used to.
Take a look at this.
Oh, wow! You have such
pretty handwriting!
Thanks, I guess,
but can you read it?
'Course I can!
Would you mind reading
it out for me, then?
"Hakuto Kunai."
"Aku."
"One plus one is two."
And the last one is "G. A. M. E."
Is that right?
That's right.
[OONO] Hmm. So we speak
the same language
and we read the same language,
but she's never heard of Japan.
I don't really get it,
but that's convenient at least.
[KUNAI] So how does this
Wishing Shrine work anyway?
Is it like one of those places
where you toss in money
and pray for good luck?
[AKU]
It's much more than that.
The Cherub used it
to seal away Greole.
I don't know the
details, myself,
but it must be very powerful!
"Powerful" like how?
It grants wishes. And not like
the "good luck" kind of stuff,
but real miracles that
can change the world!
Sounds like a fairy tale.
You could even wish for
more power, if you wanted to.
Then you could plunge the whole
world into a sea of darkness.
Why would I wanna do that?!
[KUNAI sniffs]
[KUNAI]
That's a bad sign.
I'm afraid it might
dangerous in there.
You wait outside for now.
[AKU]
Um, okay.
[KUNAI]
That explains the smell.
I figured as much.
Bleh!
[IDOL]
Interesting.
So this is our Demon Lord.
[gasps]
[IDOL] I've granted many wishes
in my time at this temple,
but I believe this
one shall be my last.
[KUNAI] Wait a second.
You know something, don't you?
It's like you were
waiting for me!
Were you the one
who summoned me here?
[IDOL] I played a part,
but it was their will.
"We wish for the Demon Lord
to descend upon this
world," they said.
These guys, you mean?
And now they're dead?
So did they summon
Greole here, too,
or was that someone else's idea?
[IDOL] Greole broke the
seal with his own power.
No wish was necessary.
Upon his revival,
he took control of the
surrounding forest
and demanded sacrifices from all
the villages in its vicinity.
[KUNAI]
Sacrifices.
[IDOL] These people wished
for the Demon Lord's descent,
but Greole appeared in order
to prevent the summoning.
He slaughtered every
last one of them.
Sorry. That's not my problem.
I need you to send me back!
[IDOL]
I'm afraid I cannot.
That would defy the
last wish that I granted.
You're the boss!
Just change the rules!
[IDOL]
I cannot grant your wish,
but seeing as you are
my final visitor,
I shall give you this.
[gasps]
Take it back! It's ugly!
This isn't a gift at all!
You're trying to
punish me, aren't you?
[IDOL] I pray that you find
your way home, in due time.
I was once a beautiful
sight to behold‐‐
a symbol of purity.
But many years of granting
wicked wishes to humans
turned me into this.
[IDOL] Yet still, I pray
that your wish comes true.
[sighs] Well, got this
stupid ring, but what now?
[footsteps]
[AKU gasps]
[AKU] How was it? Did you
have your wish granted?
Did you wish to rule
the world after all?
Or for depravity to
poison the land?
[KUNAI]
Yoga! Yoga!
‐‐[AKU] Ow, ow, ow!
‐‐[KUNAI chuckles]
[AKU]
What did I say wrong? Stop!
[KUNAI] Aku, are there any big
cities somewhere in the area?
There's the capital.
Right here in the
Kingdom of Holy Light.
Works for me.
Think you can draw
me a map, maybe?
Please don't leave me!
I mean, do you think you
could take me with you?
Huh? You really wanna
hang out with me?
Well, it would be nice.
I, uh, can't exactly
live in the village now,
since I was cast out
as a sacrifice and all.
[OONO] I know hardly
anything about this world.
Might be handy
having her as a guide.
Heh. I don't mind. Let's go.
[gasps] Thank you so much!
If it's all right,
could we go back to my
village for a second
before we set off?
I don't have much, but I'd
like to grab something.
[KUNAI]
That's fine.
Now hop on, and no
complaints this time.
It won't take long with
as fast as you run!
[KUNAI]
Question.
If the situation is bad enough
that people are
sacrificing each other,
then why hasn't this
Capital or whatever
done anything to help?
Well, our village is pretty far
away from the Holy Capital, so.
[KUNAI]
I see.
So we're in the
middle of nowhere.
[AKU]
Um, Mister Demon Lord?
Could you tell me about
the place you come from?
Uh, let's just say
it's way out there.
All of the land near my
village was made barren
thanks to a curse from Greole.
Even the water underground
is dirty and poisonous.
That's why I was so happy
when I was able to take a
bath in that beautiful lake.
I've never seen such
clean water in my life.
Oh, we're almost there.
It's quiet today.
Just go right in.
[AKU]
I live over that way.
[VILLAGERS chuckle]
[OONO]
Stealth Stance.
[VILLAGERS chuckle]
Huh?
[OONO]
Player messaging feature.
[KUNAI] Private message
to Aku. Can you hear me?
[AKU] Huh? The mean
voice of the Demon Lord
is echoing in my head!
[KUNAI]
It's gruff and cool! Not mean!
Never mind.
Do what you have to do.
I'll be hiding nearby.
[AKU]
Um, okay!
[AKU gasps]
I thought the trash
got taken out,
but it looks like it came back!
If I recall, you were
supposed to be a sacrifice!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
That hurts! [gasps]
Those bastards!
[gasps]
[RING] If they displease
you, then purge them.
I have the authority
to dispose of anyone
you deem unfit to
inhabit this world.
What the hell?
I'll do that in‐game,
not in real life!
[RING]
If you didn't crave that power,
why did you create that game,
that world, in the first place?
You made it twisted, rotten,
drowning in death
and destruction.
Just like you wanted.
[KUNAI growls]
[RING] It is you who is
the root of all evil.
If I am a fiend who purged
over four million
lives from the world,
then what are you?
Nothing less than the devil...
This's all in my head!
I am not gonna listen to you!
[KUNAI grunts]
[AKU gasps]
Just who the hell are you?
[VILLAGER 1B gasps]
It can't be.
Are you're one of
Greole's underlings?
Please, spare our poor village!
Wasn't our sacrifice
good enough for you?
Hurry up. Go get
your stuff, Aku.
Um, yes, sir, Demon Lord.
[gasps] What did you say?
[ALL] He's a Demon Lord?
The Demon Lord?
[OONO] You just had to open your
mouth right then, didn't you?
[VILLAGER 1C]
You brought him here?!
Are you trying to kill us,
you piece of trash?!
You're nothing but a plague!
Take your Demon Lord
and get out of here!
[KUNAI growls]
[VILLAGER 1D gasps]
The lord will hear about this!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
We're leaving.
That's a good idea.
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Sorry you couldn't get your
stuff after all the trouble.
I'll be okay.
I'm not so sure about
the villagers, though.
I was just warmin' up the place.
They're probably having
fun with their big bonfire.
Think of it an act of kindness
to spice up their
boring little lives.
Mister Demon Lord?
I don't understand.
Why would you do this
for someone like me?
Don't put it that way.
And don't let other people tell
you what you're worth, either.
You're doing a fine job in this
rotten world, if you ask me.
[gasps]
Do you really think so?
What do you say?
You have to admit, that was fun.
Um, kind of.
But I feel like it's bad
for me to laugh too much.
[BOTH laugh]
[KUNAI] Now, point me to
the capital, partner!
All right! Thanks for
letting me tag along!
[OONO] Coming to another
world reminds of something
an Infinity Game
player said once.
"These days, it seems like
everyone and their dog
is getting sent to
another world."
Since this is such
a common occurrence,
I'd like to say something
on behalf of all the people
in my same predicament.
[OONO inhales]
[OONO]
If we're not coming back,
at least let us wipe
our hard drives first!
[AKU] What's a hard drive,
Mister Demon Lord?
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 2.
"Golden Luna."