[BAR PATRONS chattering]
A Demon Lord, huh?
What's he like? Is he
good‐looking or what?
Oh, yeah, that fancy old dude?
A total daddy.
He could so get it
any way he wanted.
[laughs]
Yukikaze, you never
change a bit, do you?
You could grab any guy by the
balls and he'd be all yours.
Would you stop?
He's the freaking Demon Lord!
Don't you even know
what that means?
And anyway, I'm fairly positive
you're not his type.
How do you know that?
I could give him beautiful
Demon Lord babies.
All right, that's it,
has somebody spiked
your milk or something?
The point being
there were something like 300
Sandwolves there, you know!
And that guy literally
scorched the whole pack
in less than a second!
[MIKAN] A person like
him invites disaster.
Mikan,
did you already forget how that
fancy old dude saved your life?
[MIKAN grunts]
Okay, fine, that's fair, but...
Ah, I'll happily pay
him back with my body!
Live your best life,
just leave me way out of it!
Man, my head hurts.
Iei, there you are. More ale!
Sure thing!
[YUKIKAZE] And I want some
more of that creamy milk stuff
in my belly!
[SATANIST 5A]
Walking.
You had Hades and yet you
accomplished so little?
[SATANIST 5B] Look, you may
be good at giving orders,
but when it comes down to it,
you're a total coward.
No, that Dragonkin
just happened to
possess powers out
of the ordinary.
That's all it was.
[UTOPIA]
To be perfectly honest,
the appearance of this
Demon Lord concerns me
quite a bit more than
the Dragonkin ever could.
Lord Utopia.
Though it's true we
revived the Demon King,
there are rumors that he was
killed by this Demon Lord.
In any case,
it seems Hades requires
more sacrifices and power.
We'll destroy the capital
by allowing Hades to consume
everything, both good and bad.
Greole, that useless,
incompetent fool...
[UTOPIA]
How could he have stumbled over
such a tiny pebble?
So, uh, what's that village?
Seems like a pretty desolate
place from the looks of it.
That happens to be my village.
Huh?
What? It's my territory!
So you're fine with the way
things are going here?
Have you seen it?
I have no interest in
running a stupid territory.
Besides, someone they
sent from the church
is officially overseeing it,
so it's really none of
my business, anyway.
[OONO]
Now I get it.
Luna's just the public face
used to rally support.
Probably a blessing.
She's good at magic but she'd
suck at running a territory.
Someone like her would
raise taxes like crazy
and cause a revolt
faster than she could say
"let them eat cake."
I imagine she'd get herself
slapped into the stocks
her very first day on the job.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
[OONO] They probably dumped
this particular land on Luna
to keep her away from
the better areas
and their own
interests elsewhere.
[KUNAI]
Message.
Yu.
I have a strong suspicion
that the church is
manipulating Luna like
she's no more than a puppet.
What do you think?
[YU]
I agree.
The nobility and
the church brass
most likely decided to take
full advantage of her naivete
by choosing to stick her with
the most problematic land.
[KUNAI]
Mmm.
In which case,
they can't really complain
if we take this rejected
piece of earth, right?
[YU]
You plan to use this village?
[KUNAI]
Why not?
It's Holy Maiden territory,
so no one should interfere.
That's pretty convenient.
[AKU gasps]
[LUNA gasps]
[BOTH]
Huh?
Luna. I'd like to borrow
a corner of the village.
[LUNA gasps]
Demon Lord, what is it
you're planning to do here?
Nothing much.
Just considering
possibly running
a doctor's office
for the people.
Oh, you mean with Miss Yu?
If Miss Yu works as a doctor,
people from all over
the kingdom will come!
[KUNAI]
Mm.
Well, Chief?
How about around this area?
[KUNAI]
Hmm. It looks a little cramped.
See, I was thinking about
building a hot spring resort
right next to it.
A hot spring, huh?
That sure sounds lovely.
[OONO] Let's be real,
it's hard to find anyone
who hates hot springs.
So, if I open up a hospital
and hot springs together,
I could rake in double
the income! Boom!
I could even sell soap in
some kind of package deal
and have a really
nice little business!
[ALL]
Hm?
Well, if it isn't Miss Luna.
It's so nice of you
to come and see us.
[PRIEST 5A]
Wait a second!
It's that man from
the wanted posters!
Yup! The Demon Lord.
And I've forced him
to cooperate with me!
Am I right to assume you're
the one appointed here
by the church?
From this day forward,
Luna and I will be looking after
this village together, thanks.
Get back to the
church or whatever
and pass the news on
to whoever needs it.
Uh, pardon me, but shouldn't
we really be discussing this
with my superiors first?
Superiors?
I'm afraid I'm not
exactly following.
Luna is the rightful
lord of this territory
and she wishes to run things
her own way from here on.
But it kind of sounds to me
like you're suggesting
the church and your highly
questionable superiors
are the true lords of this
territory and this village.
Oh, no, no, no, no, not at all!
Of course this village belongs
exclusively to Miss Luna!
[KUNAI]
Mm.
Well, I believe you've answered
your own question, then.
Now, run along and do as I said.
[PRIEST 5A]
Hiyah!
So, you can be a
surprisingly smooth talker
when it comes down to it, huh?
Don't worry about a thing.
If you just leave it all to me,
I'll help this village
get back up on its feet.
So, um, do you think my
allowance could go up at all?
Of course. I promise you that.
Kyon, how're the
carrots over there?
Not good.
They're too skinny
to sell for much.
How are yours over there?
[MOMO grunts]
It's bad here, too.
We need to buy more
Water Crystals.
Can we? They're so pricey now.
Earth Crystals, too.
The soil is so bad
that without Crystals,
there's no way we'll be
able to grow carrots.
[MOMO]
No one can grow them but us,
so at least we can get a
good price from the harvest.
But when I think of how
many Crystals we'll need...
[KUNAI] What's the deal with
the rabbit‐eared people?
They're a race called "Bunnies."
What they say is that long ago,
the Cherub loved
and adored them.
There aren't many of them,
but they've all gathered
here to live together.
Adored, huh?
Almost seems more like they're
being quarantined here.
Because the Kingdom
of Holy Light...
...kind of hates all the
other races except humans.
[KUNAI grunts]
[LUNA squeals]
Hold on, what did
you do that for?
Heh. No reason, really.
Just a little friendly
support to cheer you up.
Stop lying to me!
You're a pervert and all you
wanted was to touch my butt,
am I right? I'm right, aren't I?
You know I'm right!
Could you save your
dreams for bedtime?
I, for one,
would like to go hear
what the Bunnies have to say.
[groaning]
Oh, so you're already
bored with my butt
and now you're gonna go
after the Bunnies' butts!
You're the perviest demon
lord in the whole world!
Yes, I can see the water
shortage is causing you trouble.
Is there anything you
can do, Demon Lord?
You knew good and well that
your vassals were in need
and yet you turned your
back and didn't help them.
Not exactly model
Holy Maiden behavior.
It isn't my fault, okay?
I was always taught to
keep my pretty little hands
out of the dirty workings
of the day‐to‐day.
So, you said your
name was Kyon, right?
Is there a well for
water in this village?
[KYON]
Um, yes, there is! Hop!
[OONO]
Hop?
[GIRLS] Hop, hop,
bunny, bunny, hop, hop!
This is prob'ly obvious,
but why do you use
the word "hop" so much?
Oh, we've just learned
humans get pretty disappointed
unless we finish with that, hop!
[KUNAI] Well, you can
drop it for me, okay?
Did you say your name was Momo?
You can skip all
the "hopping," too.
Got it, bunny.
[OONO]
No, you don't get it at all!
What the hell's wrong
with these people?
The water well is this way. Hop!
You guys are killing me.
Please, just guide
us there, already.
Okay, what kind of
shape is it in?
Not good.
The underground water vein
is completely exhausted,
and it's likely that
digging any deeper would be
a complete waste of
time and resources.
Ah, that figures.
But we don't have
the budget to go out
and buy more Water
Crystals, bunny.
We're in trouble, hop.
[LUNA] He's gonna do something
crazy again, but what?
What'll we do?
[OONO] Let's see, a Pulley
Wheel is a low‐level item,
so it's only five skill points.
When you play Infinity Game,
plastic bottles
filled up with water
are the primary recovery item.
[OONO]
In areas with water wells,
you could use a Pulley Wheel
in order to draw the water up.
Cool, I've got 265 skill points.
Even if I build the field
hospital and hot springs,
I'll have some left over.
[KUNAI grunting]
Well, shall we
get started, then?
One low‐level item.
Creation.
C'mon!
[ALL gasp]
[YU chuckles]
I'm getting scared now, hop!
What even was that, bunny?
How do you do it?
Where the heck do you
get all that stuff from?
I suppose the simplest answer is
a fragment of my intelligence.
Right. That makes total sense.
All right, we should
probably go ahead
and get this thing attached.
I'll help. I love a challenge.
if the well's exhausted,
isn't it kinda pointless
to add a Pulley Wheel, hop?
It's okay.
You can trust Mister Demon Lord,
he knows what he's doing.
Using this special
Pulley Wheel of mine
is guaranteed to
produce water every time.
The state of the well
doesn't even matter.
I don't think I understand
what you're saying, bunny.
Well, I don't understand why
you say "bunny" all the time,
so we're even.
What's the weirdo
doing this time?
Aku, could you bring
up some well water?
Sure! I'll try!
[KUNAI]
See, by twisting this wheel,
even Aku can draw water
with relative ease.
And all I have to do is
turn it like this, right?
You're nuts! You can't draw
water from a dry well!
[AKU gasps]
[gasps]
Look, it's water!
Huh?!
Okay, what's the meaning
of this, Demon Lord?
It's just like he
said it would be.
it's a total cinch
for me to fetch water!
Momo! Look at this!
There's tons of water now!
Are you kidding?
How is that possible?
[OONO] You guys can
speak normally after all!
[OONO] As I thought,
it's regular water.
I would definitely
have to rethink my plan
if it was water that
recovered HP, but...
Then again, if Water Crystals
are valuable enough to be sold,
it probably wouldn't be the
smartest move in the world
to let this go public.
Well? You gonna explain?
Why's water suddenly coming out
just because you
added that thing?
[KUNAI] This is a magic
Pulley Wheel from my homeland.
As you can see,
it draws water from even
the most dried up wells.
I'm sure it's not hard
to understand how valuable
an item like this can
be for a community.
[BOTH]
Mm.
Honestly, it wouldn't be outside
the realm of possibility
for a war to break
out over this thing.
[OONO] The fact that it's
such a low‐level item
is beside the point.
[BOTH gulp]
We'll keep the secret in
this village forever, hop!
We can't thank you enough!
Now we can grow healthy
carrots again, bunny!
[OONO] They're saying
it on purpose now!
Why must they torture me?
Anyway, let's see. The next
thing you need for farming is...
I need a mid‐level item.
Creation.
[KUNAI]
Fertilizer.
I assume you know
how to use this.
I'm counting on you to do
whatever needs to
be done with it.
Momo, look!
This fertilizer is amazing!
Oh, wow! It's overflowing
with blessed power!
[OONO] Well, this should
lighten up the mood
in the village for
a bit, at least.
We can fix it up all we want,
but no one's gonna come here
if the whole place is just
a bunch of downer bunnies.
Just like the thing
with the tea bowl.
it's hard to process that
such utter pieces of crap
can be so valuable here.
Kinda unbelievable.
[KUNAI]
Hm?
So. I've been thinking...
...that I guess you must
have some good in you.
Huh?
You're smarter than that.
It isn't out of the goodness
of my heart or whatever.
Everything I do is for a reason.
Then hat's your reason now?
Oh, I bet I know!
You wanna do nasty
things to the Bunnies!
[KUNAI sighs]
You're being dumb.
Surely you understand
that somebody has to
operate the hospital
and hot springs, right?
The only think I want to do
to the Bunnies is employ them.
Like this.
Ohh? Well, if it helps
my village develop
and if it raises my allowance,
then I guess I've
got no complaints.
That's good,
because I'm just laying down
the groundwork for now.
We'll do more once we
return from the capital.
You better be planning to spoil
my brains out while we're there!
Lots of clothes
shopping, am I right?
[KUNAI] Why should I
have to be dragged into
clothes shopping with you?
My goodness,
isn't that something.
So Miss Luna is taking over
the church‐run territory...
...because she would prefer to
handle it all on
her own, correct?
We should be pleased.
I admit, I'm worried about her.
The one calling
himself Demon Lord‐‐
I'm afraid that he may be
deceiving her, greatly.
Oh, don't worry.
If that bad man
bothers you so much,
you know I'd be more than happy
to discipline him
myself for you.
Miss Luna has obviously
chosen to trust this person.
I don't believe we have the
right to interfere with that.
[sighs] That's a crock.
Isn't his face already
plastered on wanted posters
all over the city?
Dona, that's because of the
damage that was caused in town.
You know what that's about.
You wish to punish
someone Miss Luna trusts
because of a rumor.
Please, you know full
well that Blitzo reported
one of his remote villages
was burnt to a crisp!
Besides, didn't this Demon Lord
person completely destroy
Miss Luna's escort?
[MARSHALL] According to all
the reports I've received,
only a single house in the
village was actually burned.
I think perhaps it could be that
Blitzo exaggerated the incident.
Come now!
Are you telling me that you
don't trust the word of a noble?
Trust is earned.
I bestow it based upon
a person's merit,
not their status.
As far as I'm concerned,
the reports from my
subordinates are more likely
to be accurate than
anything Blitzo says.
It's a rare thing for her to
act upon something on her own.
For the time being, I believe
we should wait and see.
Yes, of course!
If that's what the
Holy Maiden prefers.
As you wish.
[DONA groans]
What an insufferable person.
[DONA]
He is the worst!
[KILLER QUEEN grunts]
I heard you had a rough
time the other day.
I'm glad you're okay.
You ran into Luna in
the city of Yahoo, right?
How did she seem to be doing?
The report I received said
that she was traveling
with this man who's
calling himself Demon Lord,
so now I'm worried sick.
A Dragonkin got involved
in the whole mess
somehow as well,
apparently, so...
I'm in love.
[WHITE gasps]
For real, I think I'm
in love with that man.
I can't stop thinking about
how perfectly cool he was.
Wait, hold up.
Just what exactly are
you saying right now?
Are you... Are you actually
referring to that Dragonkin?
His crazy speed and that
beautiful fighting spirit.
His shock wave that
literally embodied
the form of a freakin' dragon!
Um, but, Queen,
isnt it hard to believe
that there was a
real Dragonkin there?
Let alone one who embodies
the form of a dra‐‐
[WHITE gasps]
You wouldn't be
spoutin' that nonsense
if you'd been there
to see him, like I was!
His strong, powerful fists!
His striking figure!
His impossibly
magnificent good looks!
And his cool lines!
Could we calm down a bit?
You gutless worms are too
early to face the dragon
by around a thousand years.
[gasps]
[KILLER QUEEN screams]
He's way too cool for me!
[KILLER QUEEN sobs]
[KILLER QUEEN]
I'm rude and I pick fights
and my language is pure trash,
but he really looked
at me as a woman!
Zero Kirisame! [giggles]
I've gotta go hurry
and find Mister Zero!
[gasps] I wanna bury
my face in his clothes!
There's no way he doesn't
smell incredible!
What the?
Will someone please explain to
me what is happening right now?
Queen and Luna are both
acting totally weird!
[AKU, LUNA giggling]
[AKU]
Demon Lord,
that Pulley Wheel
is amazing, hop!
[KUNAI]
Heh. Nothing's impossible for‐‐
Wait, what?
[LUNA]
Good grief,
how can water come out
of a dry well, bunny?
[KUNAI]
Hey!
[YU]
Chief. I've been wondering.
Do those Bunnies have human
ears as well as rabbit ones?
And if so, what's the purpose?
Hop, hop, hop, hop!
[KUNAI]
Not you, too!
[OONO]
Phew, just a dream.
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 6.
"Turmoil in the Capital."