[PATRONS chattering]
[MINK] Hey, Organ, do you
think it could really be true
that a Dragonkin
showed up in Yahoo?
No, it just seems ridiculous.
But you never know. There are
no guarantees in this world.
[MINK] I know! Sounds like
some kinda fairy tale.
A Dragonkin taking
a stand against evil.
If there really was one,
the Beast Kingdom would be all
over it, that's for certain.
[MINK]
You never know.
Maybe he's a wild
Dragonkin or something.
Don't be absurd.
Why is the union of Human
and Dragon celebrated,
but a Human and Demon?
They're detested and persecuted.
What a ridiculous,
illogical world this is.
I know the Dragonkin is
great and all, Mink,
but I recommend this one, here.
[MINK]
Hm.
[ORGAN]
Huh?
[IEI] Check it out. This man is
calling himself "Demon Lord"!
So, one thing's for sure.
If you hang out with him,
you can expect to get into
plenty of shenanigans!
Oh?
[MINK giggles]
I can feel the waves of
destiny crashing over me!
My right eye is throbbing!
I can see it! I can see it all!
By the hands of that man,
the future of our world
will plunge into chaos!
Come on, Organ!
I think we should perform
a blood oath, right here!
The coming chaos is going to be
darker than either
of us can imagine!
You do know you're a priest.
What the heck are
you talking about?
If I'm not mistaken,
aren't those the S‐Rank
adventurers, Mink and Organ?
It's true the Demon Lord
may be out of our league,
but I have a feeling
those two could handle him.
That old man is
mine and mine alone.
Nobody else lays a
hand on the hot Demon.
‐‐[music playing]
‐‐[PATRONS chattering]
I'll admit, this place is
pretty impressive, Luna.
I know! Great, right?
I mean, it's one of my
favorite spots for a reason!
‐‐[KUNAI, YU gasp]
‐‐So‐‐
Welcome, Miss Luna.
How wonderful to see you.
Thank you for visiting us again.
[LUNA]
Thank you.
But today, we've come to
celebrate a special occasion
for one of my friends here.
So, please keep that in mind.
Oh, yes, of course.
Well, let's raise a glass
and start the evening
with a toast to Aku's leg.
[ALL]
Cheers!
Congrats. You must be so happy.
[YU]
Congratulations, Aku.
Thanks, I almost can't
believe it's real!
Aku, this day belongs to you,
so just forget about manners
and eat as much as you want!
Thanks!
[LUNA giggles]
[KUNAI sighs]
[OONO]
I guess we should stick with
less sophisticated
fare from now on.
[OONO]
If this is a celebration,
I'm thinking it's about time
I make it feel like one.
'Scuse me, young man.
Could you be persuaded
to do me a favor?
Yes. Of course, sir.
I need for you to
arrange to have someone
bring this over to my table.
Whoa! What the heck?
[KUNAI]
Item Construct!
[YOUNG MAN 06A screams]
[BOTH]
Huh?
Aku, a special surprise,
just for you.
Wow!
Demon Lord, is this candy?
Aww, it's so cute I
can hardly handle it!
Yu, would you mind
doing the honors?
Sure, happy to.
It's delicious!
And sweet!
And so cute!
Right?
It's so yummy. It almost
melts in my mouth!
My goodness.
I think this must be what
happiness tastes like, Chief.
[ALL giggle]
[SHRIMPFRY]
You look like you're having
quite the grand old time, Luna.
Huh?
What the‐‐ Madam's here?
[SHRIMPFRY chuckles]
[OONO] What's the deal
with this super‐rich lady?
Is her entire body sparkling?
[SHRIMPFRY] Forgive me for
interrupting when you're
obviously in the midst of
enjoying yourselves.
Greetings, Madam.
I'm afraid that you
and I have never met.
I'm Hakuto Kunai,
at your service.
[SHRIMPFRY]
Dear me!
I haven't even
introduced myself yet!
I'm Shrimpfry Butterfly.
Charmed, I'm sure!
[OONO]
Is she kidding with that name?
Please, Madam,
would you care to sit down
and join us for dessert?
Wait, what're you doing? Why?
Oh, my.
For the rumored Demon Lord
to invite me, personally.
How very exciting this is!
[chuckles]
[OONO]
She knows all about me
and yet she still
came over to talk?
She must be a shrewd one.
[KUNAI]
Luna, who is this 'Madam'?
[LUNA gasps]
I can't believe this.
Now I'm hearing his
repulsive voice in my head!
[KUNAI] Okay, "repulsive" was
unnecessary, don't you think?
Luna, dear, is anything wrong?
Uh, no, nothing at all,
I'm totally great!
[KUNAI sighs]
If you haven't figured it out,
one of my skills is to
communicate without being heard.
[LUNA]
Obviously, I knew that! Duh.
Madam is kind of
the central figure
for all the wives
of the nobility.
She has tons of connections,
and she's hugely influential
amongst the nobles.
[KUNAI] So, you're saying
you would consider her
the queen of high society?
[LUNA]
Yeah, that's right.
And she'd be a dangerous enemy.
[KUNAI]
Good. I've got an idea.
If I can somehow manage
to gain her trust,
then we'll have an
unbeatable ally.
Which would be invaluable.
[LUNA gasps]
You see, Madam.
we've gathered here tonight
in order to celebrate
the healing of our
little Aku's injury.
Perhaps you would like to offer
your congratulations, as well?
Oh, my, that's just wonderful!
Congratulations to you, Aku!
Uh, thank you so much,
that's kind of you!
So, tell me, is this your first
time in the city, little one?
It is, yes!
It's beautiful!
I can hardly believe
I'm even here.
It's just like a dream!
Well, aren't you adorable?
You're such a sweet
and earnest young lady.
Oh, thank you, Madam.
I know. She really is, right?
I'm proud to have
her as my friend!
No, come on, stop,
you're way too kind!
And what do you think about
our city, Mister Demon Lord?
It's truly spectacular.
But it's also straightforward
and easy to understand.
Compared to some of
the impoverished lands
I've passed through
on my travels,
the Holy Capital's prosperity
is a wonder to behold.
[SHRIMPFRY laughs]
You're absolutely correct.
In fact, it's not at all unusual
for one to hear the many
lands of the kingdom
compared to either
Heaven or Hell.
I don't think that could be
any closer to the truth.
However, I believe
there might be a way
to resolve that
troubling disparity.
Well, I would love
to hear your opinion.
You're obviously a wise man.
It's a simple concept, actually.
All we have to do is transform
every last land into Heaven.
If we succeed, the country's
problems will evaporate.
It's that easy.
[SHRIMPFRY]
Goodness, this seems like
a rather large‐scale
proposition.
Madam, trust me,
if I was sitting at the
head of this kingdom,
I could get it done
within a few short years!
My.
[KUNAI]
But come, come, enough of these
boring political problems,
don't you agree?
Besides, there's
another kind of Heaven
that I'd like to
introduce you to.
That sounds intriguing!
And what exactly is this
"Heaven" you speak of?
[KUNAI]
It's this right here.
Some soap?
[LUNA] Oh! That soap is
seriously the best thing, ever!
It washes away dirt like magic
and leaves your skin
so clean it sparkles!
[SHRIMPFRY]
Magic.
Sparkling, huh?
[KUNAI]
Nice assist, Luna!
[SHRIMPFRY]
Hm...
[SHRIMPFRY] It's true, the skin
of all these ladies here
is dazzling. There's
no denying that!
I would sincerely urge you
to give it a try tonight.
I think you're going
to be astonished
at how well it actually works.
I may just!
Thank you so much for such a
wonderfully thoughtful gift,
Demon Lord!
[KUNAI chuckles]
Oh, please.
There's no need to thank me for
such a trivial thing as that.
But I am planning to open a hot
spring in the village of Rabby
sometime in the
very near future.
Now, that'll be a place
where your entire self
will be entirely revived!
Revived! Well, my goodness!
I appreciate a man
who makes bold claims.
You will find that no idea of
mine is lacking in substance.
Not a single one is
ever just for show.
And that's because every word
that comes out of my mouth,
I make into reality.
It won't be just an
ordinary bath, you see.
There will be carbon dioxide
baths, vase baths, stone saunas,
electric baths, herbal
baths, salt saunas,
and so much more for
the guests to enjoy!
Not only will it help
exhaustion, stiff muscles,
and cold sensitivity,
but your skin is guaranteed
to feel years younger
when you're done!
Please! I'm sold!
You simply must let
me come and visit!
Luna, let's keep this a secret
from my sister, Oysterfry.
Oh, I'm sorry, Madam.
I guess that means you're still
not getting along with
your sister, huh?
I'm in the same boat
as you, I'm afraid.
Sometimes, sisters have a very
hard time seeing eye to eye.
[OONO]
There's an "Oysterfry," too?
Get over yourself!
You're both fried!
[ALL gasp]
[PATRONS screaming]
[YOUNG MAN 06A pants]
Satanists! The city
is under attack!
[PATRONS screaming]
Finally, some entertainment.
That oughta spice this
dinner party up, at least.
[SHRIMPFRY gulps]
[CROWD screaming]
Okay, I get it, it's
a synchronized attack.
I guess they're not half bad.
Yu, you need to stay here
and protect the people.
While you do that,
I'll snuff out turmoil.
Of course, whatever you say.
Wait, hold up! You can't
just decide that alone.
I'm totally coming
with you, okay?
[KUNAI]
Luna, don't you get it?
It's quite possible that you're
the target of this attack.
There's no hope for
me to protect you
if you're out walking the
streets, do you understand?
What? Protect me?
I'm perfectly capable of
taking care of myself,
thank you very much.
[OONO] Will she be okay
when she's this easy to read?
Aku, there's nothing to worry
about if you're with Yu.
Just try to enjoy
the rest of your meal.
[AKU]
Okay, but...
Will you be all right
out there, Demon Lord?
[OONO chuckles]
She seems kinda like a kid
worried about her father.
[KUNAI]
It's a sideshow.
I'm just burning off some
calories after dinner.
For the record, you should
return to your meal, too, Madam!
I must say, you sure are
a confident one, aren't you?
Although, if I'm remembering
what you said correctly,
maybe that's due
to the fact that
everything you say
comes true? Hmm?
That's exactly right.
Quite frankly,
it's unfortunate for these guys
that I just happened
to be here today.
[KUNAI] Yu. If we're
going to learn anything,
we need to be able
to move easily.
[YU] So, avoid weird behavior
and boost our reputation?
[KUNAI] I love that you
always catch on so quickly.
[KUNAI]
I'm counting on you now, Yu.
[YU]
O‐Okay!
[KUNAI]
Hmm?
Did she just stutter
or something?
Nah, it's Yu we're
talking about.
[KUNAI]
Now, then!
Let me see where I should start.
[KUNAI grunts]
[CROWD screaming]
[KUNAI] They keep popping
up everywhere I go.
If you want to meet a
Demon Lord this badly,
I'll grant your wish!
[SATANISTS yell]
[yells]
[SATANISTS groan]
[MIKAN]
You asked for this!
[SATANISTS groaning]
You dirty, rotten adventurers!
Behold my Ice Slash!
No way. You're a
frozen Mikan, now.
Go, Snow Kiss!
[MIKAN]
Thanks for the save, Yukikaze!
V for victory.
Victory tastes sweet, too.
I highly recommend it,
to be honest.
Ice Hand!
[SATANISTS screaming]
Freezing up on me?
Aw, that's no fun!
Ice Splash!
[SATANISTS screaming]
Don't falter!
We still outnumber them!
Keep up the attack
for as long as you can!
[YUKIKAZE, MIKAN gasp]
This isn't looking too good.
What now, Yukikaze?
Dying a virgin was
not part of my plan.
It's pretty impressive
that you can
think about sex at
a time like this.
What's a guy like you
worried for any‐‐
[SATANIST 06A yells]
[SATANIST 06A groans]
[KUNAI]
That's a clown for you.
[YUKIKAZE, MIKAN gasp]
[KUNAI]
Would anyone else out there
care to put on a good show?
[YUKIKAZE]
My old man!
We meet again.
He's so dreamy!
Demon Lord!
‐‐[KUNAI grunts]
‐‐[SATANISTS gasp]
Demon Lord, huh?
And you dare to
stand in our way?
[KUNAI] Who do you think
you're dealing with?
Kneel before me! Champion!
[SATANISTS scream]
That's what I do
for trash like you.
Enlightenment!
[SATANISTS groan]
[KUNAI]
I show you where you belong.
Pulverize!
[SATANISTS screaming]
[SATANISTS groaning]
[KUNAI]
The truth of the matter is,
I'm completely justified in
being angry at every one of you.
Though I am a
little grateful, too.
[MERGE groans]
No, I'm not gonna die like this!
My end will be a noble one!
May disaster now befall this
cursed and terrible land!
[CARNIVAL yelling]
Huh?
So I got called here by
a bunch of puny humans?
What the heck is that about?
Hey, Yukikaze, that thing
is a Devil, right?
Yeah. The Satanists
summoned it here
in exchange for their lives.
It's not looking so good.
[CARNIVAL]
Whatever.
Looks like there are lots
of tasty snacks to eat!
How exciting!
I do believe it's time
to set the table
and let despair fill the air!
Summon the Killing Field!
[CROWD screaming]
It sounds like the turmoil
is getting a lot worse,
and, of course, now I'm getting
chills out of nowhere.
I think the Devil just
used Barrier Magic.
Meaning?
[YUKIKAZE]
It means this whole area
has been trapped and closed off.
We won't be able to escape,
not unless he's defeated first.
That's right!
It's time, kittens!
Come play with Carnival!
We'll have such
a marvelous time!
Your screams will accompany
my music perfectly!
Wail for me, my darlings!
Sing your lovely songs!
I want to savor every
last note of your terror.
[screams]
[groans] What vermin
did this to me?
I will end you!
You know, that filthy mouth
actually suits you
a whole lot better.
[CARNIVAL]
Was it you, then?
You greasy dingleberry!
[KUNAI]
What a disgrace.
A pathetic swine
with an ugly face.
Your voice is putrid
and your clothes are
absolutely ridiculous.
I'd say you were irredeemable,
but now that I really look at
you, you're good for a laugh.
I'll kill you!
I'll be honest.
This is the second time
I've run into a Devil.
The last one unfortunately
expired all too quickly.
[KUNAI]
How do you think you'll fare?
[CARNIVAL gasps]
For purely academic purposes,
I'm planning to go
no‐holds‐barred this time.
You called yourself Carnival,
isn't that right?
You ready for this Tilt‐A‐Whirl?
Wait, monsieur, I was mistaken!
I have no desire to
fight you! Please!
Oops, just realized I forgot
something kind of important.
Look, whatever that
important thing is,
I can help you with it, okay?
For real, I'll do
whatever you want!
[growls]
No, no! Please! I beg you!
I don't wanna be killed
by a human in this place!
Huh?
I'm sure you've done
your share of killing.
You should get to experience
what it's like to die for once.
It's only fair, right?
[CARNIVAL screams]
[CARNIVAL gasping]
[CARNIVAL screaming]
What filthy fireworks.
[VILLAGERS cheering]
This is you, isn't it?
Long live Demon Lord!
Seriously, you're
something else!
Mister, let me buy you
a drink sometime!
Look, folks, when you're
as good as I am,
doing something
like that is nothing.
‐‐[YUKIKAZE] Old man!
‐‐[KUNAI] Huh?
You've saved me two times now,
and I'd like to pay you back.
There's no need for that.
I had my own reasons for wanting
to do this, so no worries.
Well, at the least, could you
tell me your name, old man?
[KUNAI]
Old...
[OONO] The me in here is still
pretty young, little twerp!
Sure, why not. I'm Hakuto Kunai.
[YUKIKAZE gasps]
Hakuto... Kunai...
[VILLAGERS cheering]
Oh, I just knew it!
The red thread of fate
ties us together!
Slow your roll,
you're being stupid!
There's no way you
can trust this guy.
Jealous, Mikan?
Why the hell would I be jealous?
If you must know where
my heart truly lies,
I prefer heroes
like that Dragonkin...
[OONO] Hmm? She's into
the Dragonkin, huh?
My, how naughty.
So you prefer people
who love just ass...
[OONO]
Um, I think you said that wrong.
[MIKAN] That's not even close
to the same word, you perv!
[OONO]
Well, kinda close.
[MIKAN groans] Yukikaze!
I can't take it with you!
[OONO]
What the hell is happening?
For battle within the Game,
what you have to do is
combine all of your skills
and utilize them in
whatever ways you see fit.
So, depending on how
you combo things up,
it's quite possible to do
astronomical damage.
If you're truly an expert,
it's been said you can
even defeat a god.
[AKU sighs]
What filthy fireworks.
[KUNAI]
Huh?
[AKU] You really put on
a show, Demon Lord!
[KUNAI]
Wait, who told you that?
[AKU] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 7.
"All or nothing."