[CROWD murmuring]
[KILLER QUEEN gasping]
[CROWD cheering]
[KIRISAME]
How about it, runt?
Think you might remember
how to smile now?
[gasps]
[KIRISAME]
U‐Uh‐‐
[KIRISAME laughs]
I'll admit, you do seem happier
than you did before, runt!
[TRON]
I'm not a runt.
I'm Tron.
Tron, huh?
Now that's not a name
one hears every day!
[KILLER QUEEN]
Mr. Zero!
What're you doing?
Look, not in front of everyone.
Sorry. I just never
wanna let you go!
[KIRISAME]
Hey, hands off!
A man and a woman should show
a little more class than this.
Can't be helped!
The dragon on your back
is so freaking manly
I can't even stand it!
And that chest, too.
[KIRISAME]
Let go of me!
[KUNAI]
It's an honor to meet you,
Holy Maiden Angel White.
Nice to meet you, too.
Come.
So, what would be appropriate
for me to call you?
Oh, just "Demon Lord"
is fine by me.
It would seem it's become
my official nickname, anyway,
so I might as well embrace it.
So, are you truly
the Demon Lord
that all the old
legends talk about?
If that's how you
wanna look at it,
I suppose I am, yeah.
And just what is
your involvement
with Luna at this point?
Meeting her was a disaster
waiting to happen,
as you can imagine.
At first, I'm sure she only
saw me as some evil being.
However, we've
been able to build
a pretty wonderful
relationship since then.
[WHITE]
H‐Huh? No way!
[LUNA]
I'm ordering you to do as I say!
[WHITE] Luna, the very
definition of selfish?
He must have put some kind
of crazy spell on her!
Tell me, are you
someone who plans
to bring harm to this kingdom?
[KUNAI] That's a simple
enough question to answer.
See, back in my country, we have
this terrific old saying:
a picture is worth
a thousand words.
What it basically means is that
seeing something in person
is always better than just
having it explained to you.
That's a very good way
to look at things.
I would suggest that you not
decide what you will about me
until after you've seen my
skills and achievements.
My actions have a
pretty strong tendency
to speak for themselves,
and, true to form, they're
always louder than my words.
[WHITE] Is he planning some kind
of invasion of the Holy Capital?
[KUNAI] By the way, there's a
favor I'd like to ask of you,
if it's no bother.
What would that be?
Well, truth is, I've been
thinking about doing
a little research on the Seraph.
So, if there's a
library available,
I was hoping you'd
let me make use of it.
[gasps]
[WHITE] Wait, why does he want
to know about the Seraph?
Is it to figure out her weak
spots so he can kill her?
He's so bold and shameless,
he's actually asking
permission right to my face!
You can use it as you wish.
You're welcome to.
Although, I hope you'll
forgive me if I insist
on not speaking about
the Seraph, myself.
[KUNAI]
I see.
Yes, that's perfectly fine.
I've been finding it
a little challenging
to carry on conversation
with a sacred being
such as yourself, anyway.
Now, it seems like a very
good time to excuse myself.
Thank you, this meeting
seemed quite productive.
Yes. I would tend to agree.
It has been enlightening
for me, as well.
Was it you...
who defeated the Demon King?
I still don't understand
how you people can
call that thing a Demon King.
To me, he just seemed
like a cheap imitation.
[door opens, closes]
[WHITE sighs]
[WHITE] Even the Demon King
was nothing to him!
[sighs]
[OONO] Man, that woman's
a total knockout!
And I must say,
she seems uniquely sensible
for a Holy Maiden.
Actually, maybe the other
two are the odd ones.
[OONO] Thanks to the
fight the other day,
I've got 1,249 skill points.
Not only can I summon an aide,
I can build the hospital
and some hot springs
and still have extra
points left over.
Using the Omni Travel
system command,
I can travel back to an area
I've gone to before, instantly.
[laughing]
Huh? That wicked laugh
can only mean one thing.
Demon Lord is here!
Huh?
[AKU] How was it? How was your
talk with the Holy Maiden?
It went really well, kid!
[AKU giggling]
[OONO] We're feeling more like
father and daughter every day!
[KUNAI]
Hmm. I just don't get it.
This angel stuff sounds like
some kinda western fairy tale.
Well, at least the
pictures in this book
are super pretty,
don't you think?
Yeah, If only it was
meant to be a picture book.
So, did the angels exist
from the beginning,
or were they created by someone?
That's really the question.
And why is it that they
disappeared, anyway?
The demons they fought
against seem alive and well.
Huh? I really never thought
about it that way before.
The weirdest part is,
there's not a single thing
written here about the Seraph.
They just bail or what?
Oh, no, I don't think
that's what happened at all.
I feel sure they're watching
over us from somewhere!
At any rate,
we've got plenty of time.
We'll be able to come back here
whenever we feel like it.
Okay!
I want to try to read as many
books as I can! [giggles]
[AKU]
Um, Demon Lord?
Last one. Would you be
willing to read it to me?
Huh? Destructive Fido's
Great Adventure?
What is this?
[NARRATOR 08A]
A long time ago,
there was a mischievous
dog named Fido
who used his sharp teeth to
destroy everything in his path.
One day, the villagers
decided they were
tired of his destructive
ways and drove him off.
To make ends meet,
Fido became an adventurer
and set out to explore
a nearby dungeon.
He delved deeper and
deeper into the dungeon,
tearing up other adventurers'
weapons and armor as he went.
[SMILE]
Ew, slimy.
[NARRATOR 08A] Fido came across
a slime attacking another dog.
[FIDO]
You filthy slime!
How dare you! Woof!
[NARRATOR 08A]
After saving her from the slime,
Fido spent the rest of the
night gently nibbling her.
Fido finally reached the
deepest room of the dungeon,
and there, he discovered
a trove of rare weapons,
armor, and magical items.
He carried all of
them home with him,
became a very famous dog,
and lived happily ever after.
[AKU gasps]
[KUNAI sighs]
What the heck was that?
Don't the stories in
picture books usually have
some sort of meaningful
lesson in them or whatever?
Who was the target
demographic for this thing?
At least it's got
a cute puppy in it!
[OONO]
And he went into a dungeon, huh?
[KUNAI]
You there, librarian.
Yes, can I help you?
Tell me something,
is it true that weapons and
armor drop in dungeons
the way they do in this book,
or is that not a thing?
Oh, yes! I have heard that
people find rare, ancient items
from time to time.
Huh.
[OONO]
This body of mine is pretty much
impervious to physical
attacks, so that's good.
But my weak point is magic
because that stuff didn't
exist in Infinity Game,
so it's a brand‐new
thing for me.
[OONO] I definitely
need to find some way
to raise my magic
resistance by a lot.
As soon as possible.
Aku.
Go back to the inn
without me for now.
I've got something
I need to take care of.
'Kay, see ya later!
[KUNAI sighs]
[KUNAI]
Listen, I'm a pretty busy man,
despite what you might think.
I don't have time to
play hide‐and‐seek.
Wait, you're‐‐
I found you.
[OONO]
I know this kid.
She's the one I saved
as Zero, isn't she?
Well?
What is it you
want from me, runt?
Yep, you talk like Zero
and have the same color.
Color? Wait, back up,
what're you talking about?
I just see everything
as a color.
Even emotions and souls.
What, is that some new
form of fortune‐telling?
Go bug someone else.
[thud]
Bring out Zero right now.
Sorry, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Wrong person.
Do it! You have to
bring him out! Right now!
Wait a minute, am I
missing something here?
I mean, what're you getting at?
Zero's‐‐
Well, it's just that you're
the one who saved my life,
so I want to see you!
[OONO] I've got no idea
how old this kid is,
but I can't just let
someone Zero saved
end up dying out in the streets.
That's definitely not okay.
Fine, you win.
But there are conditions
if you meet Zero.
You gonna be okay with that?
Of course. I'll do anything.
[KUNAI]
Listen, I'll tell you what.
If you obey my commands
and work hard for me,
I'll let you meet him.
What kind of thing do you
think I'd have to do as work?
Do I have to kill
lots of people?
What the hell?!
Why does everyone here have
the wrong idea about me?!
Oh, then what do I do?
Hmm. Soon enough, we're going
to feel short‐staffed
no matter how many
people we have.
If you could use your
strength and color thing
to lend me a hand, I think
I could arrange a meeting.
How does that sound? Good, runt?
My name's really Tron.
It's definitely not "runt."
[KUNAI]
A runt is a runt. Let's go.
Okay!
[KUNAI]
All right.
I take it everyone's ready
to roll? Let's get going.
Hey, Chief. Who's that
little girl with you?
[AKU gasps]
You have such beautiful hair!
[gasps] Whoa! What are you?
For real! There's
Devil in that girl!
[TRON gasps]
[OONO]
There's Devil in her?
That's too bad, 'cause we're
gonna need her in Rabby.
So just deal with it.
A Holy Maiden and Devilkin?
You're asking too much.
I think if we can manage
to turn that village around,
your sisters will see you
in a totally different light.
[gasps] I don't know.
[KUNAI] First of all,
those who are standing
at the pinnacle of a kingdom‐‐
[gasps]
[KUNAI] They should
really have the capacity
to deal with all
types of people.
If you only ever see
things in black and white,
you'll never move
forward in this life.
What is this? Why're
you preaching at me?
[KUNAI] I'm just saying, I have
high expectations, that's all.
Fine, all right then, go ahead!
Be warned!
I won't be this sweet
if she does something bad!
[KUNAI] Yu, are you
able to Omni Travel now?
[YU]
I am, Chief.
Incredible.
It feels like something
holding me down was removed.
Everyone, come here
and grab onto me.
We're jumping to Rabby Village.
[KUNAI] Yu, couldn't you
make the jump yourself?
[YU] It's nonsense
to consume 60 Power
when we have the option of only
using 30, though, Chief.
[KUNAI]
Well, you do have a point.
[KUNAI clears throat]
Here we go.
Omni Travel.
Rabby Village!
[AKU]
Wow, that was amazing!
[LUNA]
Are you kidding me?
How'd we manage to
get back to my territory
in the bare blink of an eye?
Yu, I want to start
construction right away.
Right, understood.
Hey, look! It's black
suit man, bunny!
The pulley wheel and the
fertilizer helped so much, hop!
[OONO]
Just wait.
I'll turn this village around.
By the time I'm done, it's gonna
be raining gold around here.
[KUNAI sighs] I guess this
spot will have to do.
It's time for
Rare Item Creation.
First Aid Kit.
[KUNAI]
Base Upgrade.
Field Hospital.
Hey, Chief, would you
like to go inside
and check things out together?
Good call.
[OONO]
There's no electricity,
yet everything seems
to be running just fine.
[KUNAI]
Well, is it good to go?
[YU]
Yep. We could even start today.
But what are your thoughts on
how we should deal
with charging people?
[KUNAI] This is just to have
something in place, but...
Let's start by
assigning coins to values
that we're familiar with.
And if it ends up being wrong,
then we can always
adjust it in the future.
I like your style.
With this world having so many
different values and cultures,
we don't have much choice but to
boldly take a shot in the dark.
Well, let's see, based on
my experience thus far...
Copper's a hundred yen,
giant copper is a thousand,
silver's ten thousand,
and gold's a hundred K.
And the elusive giant gold coin
is worth around two million.
[KUNAI] There's also something
called a holy lambda coin,
but depending on the season
and what the market does,
it changes value.
Regarding the
prices for treatment.
I want you to care for the poor,
but don't charge them
more than they can afford.
Trying to collect money from
people who simply don't have it
is an enormous waste of time.
As for the nobles,
charge as much as you want.
Right! Sounds like a plan.
We'll help the poor
and fleece the rich,
which means we'll gain the
support of the common people.
You do realize
that you're taking
the exact opposite approach
of the Great Empire?
Nothing's more boring to me
than treading down
a well‐beaten path.
Always feels a little more
like going backwards.
Yes. We have that in common.
Somehow, I just knew
our minds and hearts
were on the same page!
[gulps]
[OONO] Okay, I'll admit,
that was oddly cute,
but seriously, has she
always been this way?
[KUNAI]
Base. Rare Item Creation.
Walled Springs!
[OONO]
Right next to the hospital...
Hot springs, baby!
Not bad, if I say so, myself.
Three massive and
magnificent floors of fun!
Carbon dioxide bath. Vase bath.
Stone sauna. Electric bath.
Herbal bath. Even one outdoors!
And a salt sauna to top it off.
A great hall and fully‐
equipped dining room.
With beautiful lodging on
the second and third floors!
And when it comes to
Japanese hot springs,
you know you gotta have bamboo.
It's making me miss home.
[KYON] Wow, that sure
came out of nowhere, hop.
[MOMO]
It's unbelievable, bunny.
[OONO] Those two are stylish
enough and easy on the eyes.
They can work reception.
When you finish your work today,
I want you to assemble
all the villagers
and bring them here,
do you understand?
Okay, but why are we
bringing them, hop?
Well, my thought is that
in order for you to be
the best hosts for our guests,
it's important for everyone
to experience it first,
as guests, yourselves.
In other words,
you get some bathing time.
Bathing? But only wealthy nobles
can afford luxuries
like that, bunny.
[OONO] Right, in this world,
people are lucky
to wipe themselves off
with a damp cloth.
Should I open up a bath house
for commoners, then?
It's doable with the High
Level Item, Kanda River.
If we charge three copper coins,
I have no doubt it would bring
in customers by the droves!
By the way, we'll also need
to destroy and rebuild
your houses in the
very near future.
[gasps] I might have a
problem with that, hop!
Black suit man!
I thought you were nice,
but this is tyranny, bunny!
[KUNAI] Who you calling
"black suit man"?
You got something to
say about my wardrobe?
Before we know it,
we'll be building both legit
and unlicensed casinos
and anything else we
can possibly think of
to entertain all those
rich nobles out there
with more money in their pockets
than they know what to do with!
[laughing]
Black suit man's scary, hop.
Black suit man is broken, bunny.
[OONO] No matter how luxurious
the hot spring resort is,
if the employees don't
do their jobs well,
it won't amount to much.
Among the eight aides,
there was one standout
genius who could not only
immediately master
whatever you threw at him,
but also consistently
produced better results
than any of the others.
He's got a real nurturing side,
so he can watch
kids, no problem.
Also, being a gun specialist
with combat prowess
and crazy skills like his,
he'll easily be able to
protect Rabby Village
even when I'm not around.
He and Yu actually get
along pretty well, too.
Admin Privileges!
Aide Summon!
Isami Tahara.
I command you to
appear before me.
Huh? Well, if it
isn't the chief.
[OONO]
That sure takes me back.
Masaru Katou.
Yuuya Kondo.
Takefumi Nomura.
[AKU] Are those more aides
of yours, Demon Lord?
[OONO] Here's what
they are: a fencing idiot,
a hikikomori archer,
and a mixed martial
arts champion.
[AKU]
Huh?
I have to admit, I'm not exactly
sure what some of that means,
but they sound
super interesting!
[KUNAI] Next time:
Demon Lord, Retry Episode 9.
"Dancing Swindler and
the Giant Gold Coin."