Aw, hey, come on, Teach,
you don't have to be
so mean all the time.
[SHU gasps]
Hello. It's been quite
a while, hasn't it, Itsuki?
Sorry...
...Valkyrie.
You've fallen so far.
I remember a time when you were
known as Yumenosaki
Academy's Emperor.
Now here you are performing at a
pitiful concert venue like this.
It's pathetic, isn't it?
Yeah, why don't you
mind your own business?
I'm the student council
president at our school,
in case you've forgotten.
So when units are unmotivated,
it's my job to lecture them.
You think we're not motivated?
[EICHI]
Oh, dry your eyes.
Why don't you
participate in a DreFes?
I'd love for you to show
everyone what you can do--
to see you on a shining stage.
Is that what you came here
to talk to us about?
I'll get to the point.
There are people in favor
of disbanding Valkyrie.
[gasps]
It's the underground venues
at which you perform.
Makes funding your unit
seem like a huge waste.
And just who do you
think you are, man?
Can you be quiet
for a minute, please?
You want us to disband,
that's your opinion and
you're entitled to it.
It's not like the school ever
offered us very much
assistance anyway.
However, I will be the one to
decide if and when that happens.
I won't take orders
from you. Got it?
[EICHI]
You've heard of Ra*bits, right?
Of course you have,
it's your dear Nito's unit.
They remind me of a family
of newborn bunnies.
They'd get blown away
with one breath, right?
Nito's no longer a concern
of mine, so what do I care?
Maybe you don't,
but the fact remains
they're up against AKATSUKI
at the Tanabata Festival after
being defeated by them once.
I bet those bunnies'll
end up skinned and skewered.
And in the most brutal
possible way, too.
Heh.
[TORI] Day after day,
it gets worse and worse!
You're killing me!
[WATARU] To not let you
live, nor to let you die
is the basis of all
lessons, sweet princess.
[TORI]
Uh?
[WATARU] Our goal is
to fatigue the muscle
so that the fibers tear.
That way it can rebuild
bigger and stronger!
Like this, see?
--That hurts!
--Bodies are amazing!
--I can't take it!
--Don't you think?
I don't care if it's
the president's orders,
I'm done being tortured
by this longhaired pervert!
[YUZURU]
Excuse me, coming through!
[TORI]
Ow! Stop! That hurts!
Master Hibiki,
do you mind explaining
what you're doing
to the young master?
[TORI] He's not doing
anything bad to me!
Put that menacing aura away!
You look terrifying!
Are you certain about that?
Sorry, you just had me worried.
You really are too rough with
the young master, Master Hibiki.
Huh! Butler, what are you
doing with those things?
[YUZURU] I've been
helping the vice president
put up decorations for
the Tanabata Festival.
[WATARU]
Preparing for the DreFes?
I must say, that right-hand
man is quite proactive
when it all comes down to it.
[YUZURU] Of course. Anyway, so
they gave me some extra bamboo.
Young Master, would you like to
write our wishes on this paper?
[TORI]
Hmm. Only commoners do that.
But, sure. That's fine.
It's a festival, right?
[YUZURU chuckles]
[TORI]
Dear Orihime and Hikoboshi,
please make my wishes come true.
Let me see what
you wrote, Yuzuru!
[YUZURU]
Wait. Please don't look!
Sounds a bit creepy,
don't ya think?
No, don't take it the wrong way!
It's just that most
of my usual duties
have kept me away
from you lately.
Oh, well, if that's all it
is, I can grant your wish.
Rewarding slaves for their work
is one of my favorite
responsibilities.
Here! Won't you
please have a seat?
Oh, um, okay.
[gasps]
This is your reward
just for today.
Young Master.
Thank you so much.
I'm the luckiest man I know.
[YUZURU cries]
How peaceful it is now.
This must be the calm
before the storm.
I can't help but wonder...
What will happen
at that festival?
[SHU] Nito is a sinner
who betrayed his creator.
There's no reason for me
to protect him anymore.
[high-pitched voice]
"You're right as always, Shu.
But are you sure you
won't regret it, later?"
--[clapping]
--[NAZUNA] That's it!
And now turn right!
Spread those wings. Yeah!
[GROUP grunting]
[HAJIME]
Ah!
You okay, Hajime?
Yes. I'm sorry. I'm so clumsy.
Hey, that's okay!
You wanna know why?
None of us are adults yet!
Each member of Ra*bits is made
of bones that're still growing!
Yeah, he's right. Hajimechin,
please don't get discouraged.
We're all better than
we were when we started.
Let's take a quick break.
We can try again later.
--[MITSURU] Aye!
--[TOMOYA, HAJIME] Okay!
Whew.
[ANZU]
What?
[BOTH gasp]
Is there a fire in the building
somewhere? What's the matter?
[ANZU]
Something like that.
I'm trying to catch
someone before they leave.
I was hoping the one who
submitted this was still around.
Wait, Valkyrie? They're
in the Tanabata Festival?
Their application's incomplete.
Not all of them
signed, just some. So...
What a coincidence.
I was actually on my way
to go talk to those guys.
[ANZU]
So the one called Itsuki,
he's helping with the Tanabata
Festival outfits, right?
I asked him for help with mine,
so I hope that's still the case.
Good to know. Thank you
so much for your help.
It's your first DreFes, right?
Of course I'd help you.
I'm that kinda guy.
--[door opens]
--[wood cracking]
[KURO]
Everyone decent?
Itsuki, I need to talk to you.
Oh, hi there.
Wait, how did you get in here?
That door was
supposed to be locked.
My bad. Guess I
accidentally broke it down.
[MIKA] Seriously? Can you not
control your own strength, Ryu?
You wanna call me
that again, punk?
No! Sorry, Mr. Kiryu, sir!
That was very rude of me!
[KURO] I need to talk to
Itsuki. Know where he is?
Oh. He's curled up under
the blanket over there.
[KURO, ANZU]
Mm?
[MIKA] Well, it looks like Teach
is concentrating right now.
He's been focusing
on our performance
for the Tanabata Festival.
Is there anything I can
do for you since I'm here?
Not unless you know about
his progress on the outfits.
I'm here to ask about his
application. All members are
supposed to sign it and
there are a few who haven't.
[SHU]
Trés bien!
[ANZU, MIKA gasp]
[MIKA] What's going on
over there, Teach?
[SHU] I've come up with the
most perfect Festival plan!
The Tanabata Festival is
still a week away, right?
You will have everything down
perfectly by then, understood?
Hitting me with sorta short
notice this time, aren'tcha?
Know your enemy as
you know yourself,
and you shall not
fear a hundred battles.
And our enemy
doesn't know a thing
about the current Valkyrie.
That boy is such a fool.
He's been sitting on my throne
ever since I've been gone,
and I think it's
time to kick him off.
Later.
Hey, wait, where are you going?
--[sighs]
--[crash]
So... what were you saying?
[ANZU]
Really?
[ANZU] And so, with tons
of students volunteering
their time to help,
preparations for the
Tanabata Festival continued...
[ANZU] ...until finally,
the day of the festival arrived.
[WATARU] Amazing! Ladies and
gentlemen, I hope you're ready!
Let the Tanabata Festival begin!
And even though
nobody bothered to ask me,
I will still be your
MC this evening!
Give it up for...
...the one and only
Hibiki Wataru!
Let's celebrate Orihime and
Hikoboshi's romantic meeting
with a little song and dance.
Great. You can hit the
lights first, then the music.
[WATARU]
What a glorious night!
A night of miracles together!
May it be amazing with love,
blessings, and more miracles!
I need someone
to bring me my bow.
It's time to shoot down the
embarrassments of our school.
This is hardly the time or
place to be thinking about that.
In the Tanabata Festival, the
winner's the one who stays in.
We've gotta stay focused.
Of course.
Then AKATSUKI will have to
keep the stage all to ourselves.
[NAZUNA]
Don't you sound confident?
Anzu created this stage.
And her vision was that everyone
would share it with
a smile on their face.
So that goes for you,
too, grumpy pants!
I think we'll start by
kicking you off first,
then we'll make our way
straight to the top.
We're not the same
as we were before!
[WATARU] What makes this
Tanabata Festival unique
is that you can show
off your own performance
whenever you'd like,
even if that happens to be
in the middle of
an opponent's song!
The first match
will be between...
[CROWD cheering]
[WATARU]
...AKATSUKI and Ra*bits!
Ladies and gentlemen!
The first match of
the Tanabata Festival
has gloriously come to an end.
And the winner is... AKATSUKI!
[CROWD cheering]
Aw, they beat us again!
How strange. I thought
we did pretty good.
This is terrible, you guys.
I'm really sorry, Big Bro.
It's okay.
At least people got to see
what we're capable of.
So I would say that
was worth it for me.
AKATSUKI! Congrats.
Yeah, thanks, man. You guys
put up a pretty solid fight.
[NAZUNA]
Hm.
[WATARU] And now, in one of
the most exciting traditions
of the Tanabata Festival,
we will grant the wish
of someone in our
amazing audience
who voted for
the winner tonight!
And the lucky person who will
have their wish granted is...
...you! Right there!
[STUDENT A]
No way! What?!
[WATARU]
I'm waiting, Keito!
Shoot me with
your big, scary bow!
Well, get on with it.
You fool.
Don't try to make it
sound like it's easy to do.
[WATARU] Okay, well maybe add
a little "bang" sound effect.
[KEITO] That's not the
sound you make for an arrow.
Okay, fine.
B-Bang!
[CROWD screams]
Wonderful! That's what
I call an entertainer!
[SOUMA]
That was excellent, Sir Hasumi.
[KEITO] Kanzaki, I need you
to end my life right now!
That was actually pretty good.
Who's ready to see the next unit
AKATSUKI will be
competing against?
[TSUMUGI]
Excuse me!
What's this?
[TSUMUGI] Sorry, can I
please have a quick moment?
[whispering] Hear me out.
We've run into a bit of trouble.
What?
Something's going on with
our plans for the venue.
Trouble with the
workers we hired.
It's unclear. So I have
to go check it out.
If you're sure about that,
then AKATSUKI's gonna
have to leave the stage.
There are other
representatives here.
Sir Hasumi, I feel that
we should have a say in--
Can't you take a hint, Kanzaki?
Uh, hold on.
What does that mean?
We yield the right to stay
on stage and pass it to you.
[CROWD]
What?!
[KEITO]
Listen, I know this won't
erase all the hardships
we've caused.
But we'd like to do our
best to make it up to you,
even if it's just a little.
Because of where you are now,
we can leave the rest
to you without worry.
You mean it? I'm grateful.
All right, Ra*bits,
you better fight a good fight.
Do you guys still
have it in you?
I'm more warmed up now than I've
ever been! So let's do this!
To be honest, I'm actually
pretty tired, friends,
but I'll do my best!
I have no problem
continuing. I'm in.
[NAZUNA] We've become so
strong through all this.
So why don't we celebrate
with a winning round?
[ALL]
Yeah!
It doesn't matter who our
opponent is! We won't lose!
[EICHI]
Such a bold new attitude, Nito.
--[NAZUNA] Hm?
--[CROWD cheering]
[NAZUNA]
Tenshouin?
Does that mean our
next opponent is fine?
[WATARU]
Oh, my! It appears that fine
has already declared
themselves the next opponent!
Well, I suppose my job here
is done then, isn't it?
You're correct, Wataru.
Hurry up and get down here.
[EICHI]
Dinner is about to begin.
And the main dish
is fresh bunnies.
[NAZUNA]
What'll we do?
How are we up against fine?
I can't be utterly
defeated by him again!
Don't do anything! Stop, fine!
Your opponent is Valkyrie!
Or did you forget?
[MITSURU, TOMOYA, HAJIME gasp]
Hey, Teach! How long're you
gonna fiddle with that outfit?
Don't rush me, Kagehira. Sheesh.
That crowd was making me dizzy.
It's Tea-- Itsuki.
Kagehira? What brings
you guys here tonight?
[SHU] Don't you dare talk
to me so casually, traitor.
Hmph.
I guess this means
another worthless show
that cares nothing for
emotions is about to unfold.
How horribly deplorable!
Real art is dead!
Oh, you're just in time, Itsuki.
I suppose there's
no longer any need
to cut up these
pathetic rodents.
[sighs]
You can't talk about us like
we're not here! That's mean!
[NAZUNA] I am truly
grateful they came to help,
but Itsuki and
Kagehira can't perform
in front of a huge
crowd like this.
[SHU] Are you trying to think
of something insulting to say?
Try not to push
beyond your limits.
That goes for you, too, fine.
These days it seems
you've gotten carried away
thinking you can do
whatever you want.
Non!
This house of cards
will finally fall today!
Tanabata happens once a year.
Let's just enjoy it...
...with wishes in our hearts.
Hey, Itsuki--
I think you're the perfect
person to leave this with.
You're on the broadcast
committee, right?
So this should be
a smooth transition.
Are you sure, Wataruchin?
Isn't Itsuki your friend?
That doesn't matter.
It's not the first time this
turn of events has happened.
Turning pain and
stubbornness to pleasure.
Clowns should learn how
to dance while smiling!
We had to switch out MCs.
This is Nazuna Nito
from Ra*bits.
The second match
tonight will be fine,
led by the Emperor, against
the former top unit, Valkyrie!
This is a match between
the current and former suns--
a battle between old and new!
Who will come out on top?
All right, Teach. Let's go.
[SHU] Hmph. Don't ruin
this for me, Kagehira.
I'll offer you high praise
you if you perform well.
[TORI]
Whoa, that choreography!
Why did you choose
such complicated moves?
[MIKA]
I dunno.
I'm just applying the
lessons that Teach taught me.
And even if I fail at this,
I'm still his one and only
doll when I'm on stage.
And that makes me happier
than anything out here.
[YUZURU]
I do not approve.
Your body does not have
the strength to hold up.
You're making a
choice to sacrifice
any possibility of
a future as an idol.
[MIKA]
If Teach will see me as useful,
I'll happily trade
anything to help him.
My future, my life, everything!
I don't care what happens to me.
I've never seen
Valkyrie live before.
They're pretty
amazing, aren't they?
What is this?
This performance goes beyond
fine's best songs
and dance moves.
It takes you to
a higher dimension.
We blindly searched to
advance our performance,
but Itsuki, you...
[SHU] You finally remembered,
Tenshouin. Good job!
You know who the top idol of
Yumenosaki Academy truly is!
Our dream is that your sleep
is filled with nightmares
starring us every night!
[SHU laughs]
[CROWD cheering]
[KANATA]
♪ Floating, floating. ♪
Being hugged by water
is the most relaxing feeling
in the whole wide world!
Please promise me that you won't
tell Chiaki about any of this...
...'kay, Shu?
Um, a yes or no will do.
Just don't leave me
hanging over here.
You look like you're feeling
a little down tonight, Shu.
Can I give you some pats and
pets to make you feel better?
[SHU] I don't want you to touch
me with your slimy wet hands.
Though I am grateful you want
to comfort me. Thank you.
[KANATA chuckles]
[KANATA] I know it
hurts to lose in general,
but it's worse when it comes
right after such a huge triumph.
The performances we put on are
better rehearsed and designed
and far more creative
than anything fine does.
And yet more fans
would rather watch them
than appreciate real art.
It shouldn't be a shock
that we lost with fewer votes.
Those artless philistines
couldn't comprehend
what they were seeing
when we were on stage.
They have no clue
what we've accomplished.
That may be true.
But even without
artistic intelligence,
their hearts feel it.
They knew they were watching
something special and amazing.
Even if they can't describe it,
the feeling will
come back to them
when they remember this show.
It's something that stays
with you for a very long time.
The ones who understand this
best are the members of fine.
Perhaps it was your performance
that solidified
that fact for them.
Time for a new match.
The noteworthy unit who
won the DDD, Trickstar!
They'll be battling the
allies of justice, RYUSEITAI!
[CHIAKI]
Hey, where's Ryusei Blue?
Wait, now that I think about
it, Shinkai isn't here, is he?
If I had to place a bet, I'd
say he's in the fountain again.
[CHIAKI]
Ah! Someone go get him!
[NAZUNA]
What? Blue is missing?
[WATARU] There you are,
Eichi, I found you.
You shouldn't just run off
without telling someone
where you're going.
You had everyone
wondering where you were.
Oh, right, the butler
contacted me a moment ago to say
that he has escorted
the princess home
and he wanted me
to let you know.
He seemed to be in a little
more shock than usual,
so I admit I'm a bit
worried for him.
Wataru.
Eichi?
I was just thinking about the
way our match with Valkyrie went
and how great they were.
One discovery after another!
I mean, the angle
of his fingers!
It was amazing! Just like this!
Considering the
difference in our hands,
I'm impressed that I can do it.
Adjustments are still
needed, of course.
The syllables before the
chorus gave me chills!
I can still hear it now.
I'm thrilled with such
an optimal solution!
[WATARU]
Eichi.
[EICHI] And right after
that was the best part!
You know what I'm
talking about, right?
It went ta-ta-ta-tan!
Most would go ta-tan, ta-tan.
But this was just ta-ta-ta-tan.
Why didn't I think of that?
[WATARU]
Eichi!
[EICHI sighs]
Sorry.
It was just one of those
memorable performances.
I actually agree
with you about that.
But it's very windy
and you're going to catch
a cold sitting out here,
especially without
drying your sweat.
[EICHI sighs]
Yeah, you're right.
[WATARU]
See? What did I tell you?
Wataru, it seems that
you're all so loved by God.
He's never even
given me a chance.
You surpass the skills
I've desperately acquired.
You make it look effortless.
I've envied you for
a long time now.
I've envied all of you so much,
there were times when
I could barely stand it.
It goes both ways.
For us, you seem like
a terrifying mess,
yet we love you.
That make sense?
It's actually pretty confusing.
People like you can
drive out monsters.
But you've also
driven out magicians.
You're arrogant and sinful.
Traits people gain
from allowing themselves
to be controlled by their anger.
Anger you find
yourself filled with
when what you thought was
magic turns out to be skill.
And sometimes you're as
innocent as a small child.
You live your life
to the absolute fullest.
Amazing.
Someone like you
should have secured a spot
for themselves in Heaven.
But you decided you wanted
to explore Hell instead.
Even though a reality much
more beautiful than dreams
is always present in this world.
I just remembered
who taught me that.
It was you.
[ANZU]
That year, the Tanabata Festival
lasted long into the night.
It was as if all our
wishes gathered light
to be placed beneath
the beautiful stars...
[ANZU]
...until the end of time.