[ANZU] It happened a year ago,
right around the time
when everyone had first
arrived at the Academy.
So, um, if I remember
correctly, you're class B?
Isara Mao. And you are?
I'm Yuuki Makoto.
Isn't this funny?
How'd we all end up
somewhere like this
--at the same time?
--[SUBARU] Hey, guys!
Why do you all look so sad?
You need to relax!
I've got a great idea!
Since we're out here
in the woods,
let's find something fun to do!
Except, we don't really
know each other
so that might be weird.
You guys go ahead.
I've got some things
to do tonight.
[SUBARU]
Cool! Guys!
If you stand right
here and look up,
the stars in the sky
look just like
sparkly cherry blossom petals!
My dad told me about this tree!
There's a legend that says
you can tell it your wishes
and it will actually listen!
And if you bring something
important to you
and bury it at its roots,
your wish is supposed
to come true!
You have too much free time.
Why not invest some
of it in your studies?
Lighten up, Hidaka!
Life's way too short!
C'mon, guys!
[HOKUTO] Wishes and dreams
don't just "come true."
They're achieved with
consistency and hard work.
Well, sure.
Yeah, I guess
you're right. Look!
Is there a problem?
I may have imagined it,
but I could've sworn
I saw a bud blossom
into a flower just now,
as if it was listening
to what we were saying
and giving us a sign!
[SUBARU]
Wow!
[ANZU] That was the night
they met, and the moment
fate planted the
seeds of friendship.
[SUBARU, MAO, HOKUTO, MAKOTO]
Ooh!
Oh, my goodness! Those
costumes're for us?
[MAO] Cool! Those will
look amazing on stage!
Anzu, You made all of
these in only a week?
[ANZU]
Yeah.
That's what I call
a great surprise!
Hey, guys. Remember when
she was called out
by Kiryu the other day?
So here's the deal.
I always return
any and all favors.
So in exchange for letting me
borrow your handkerchief,
I'll teach you the
basics of sewing.
[BOTH gasp]
Huh? Awesome! It looks so shiny!
[MAKOTO]
And there are four stars!
I love it!
[MAO] Do those symbolize
the four of us?
They do.
Thank you, Anzu. They're great.
--[door clicks]
--[HAJIME] Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you
before you go on.
I wanted to tell you something.
Shinonon!
I heard that you're all
taking action for our sakes
after the performance
the other day.
Thanks, you guys.
It makes me so happy.
Is everyone okay?
Everyone from Ra*bits, I mean?
We are. Promise we didn't
mean to worry you.
Break a leg out there today.
I believe we could all learn
from watching the way you work.
I hope your sparkles will light
the path meant for us, too.
It's official.
The battle's begun.
Let's start this
revolution with our music.
Today is the day we
change Yumenosaki Academy
by sending out sparkles of hope!
Trickstar!
[SUBARU, MAKOTO, MAO, HOKUTO]
Yeah!
[KEITO] To the demons
who have crawled out
from the darkness. I will
bring judgment and justice
down on you.
With the blood of you fools,
I will dye this night the
color of AKATSUKI's moon!
[CROWD cheers]
[KEITO]
What's with that smug look?
Must have something
up his sleeve.
[KEITO] Does it have
something to do with
the pamphlets he passed out?
The rules for scoring
points were added
to the battle of
the bands system.
But they're not
anything unusual.
Let me think. During DreFes,
the audience can score
the units performing
by waving light sticks
that have points
assigned to each color
during the tally.
No. That can't be it.
[REI] It looks like he's
figured it out. That's right.
The two units performing
in the battle of the bands
must now compete for only
a limited amount of points.
Meaning that, if half of the
audience votes for UNDEAD,
then AKATSUKI can then
only receive points
from the remaining half.
However, if the next
unit isn't performing
under the battle
of the bands' rules,
they then can receive points
from everyone under
the normal rules.
Which makes sense,
since there won't be anyone
to fight over the points with.
Hm.
[KEITO] In the S1, the
points each unit receives
is what determines
their ranking.
AKATSUKI and UNDEAD
are competing
under the battle of
the bands system,
so they will each
score more points
against a unit
performing on their own.
[CROWD cheers]
[KEITO]
UNDEAD was a decoy!
This was your plan, wasn't it?
You mean this new
unorthodox way of scoring?
Of course. Now you know what
the Three Eccentrics
are made of.
Doesn't this take
you right back?
Looks like the plan worked!
And now for the main event
we've all been waiting for.
Please give it up for two
of our good friends, 2wink!
We jumped as soon as
you called our name!
Ta-ta-ta-ta-dah!
It's one sabotage after another.
[HINATA, YUTA]
Hey there!
[KEITO] Those twins must
be the Aoi Brothers.
The first years
in the Band Club.
[HINATA]
That's enough.
Haven't you had it with this
battle-manga competition stress?
Get out there and rock it out!
No one likes an opening act
that's too slow, right?
Oh, we're the opening act?
[HINATA, YUTA]
Sounds like someone's ego
is getting bruised!
I hope you're ready!
Because the
headliners of this S1
are about to blow your mind
and shake your soul
with their performance!
But first, I hope you'll
let us warm you up
with one of our performances!
We're 2wink!
I'll admit, your plan
threw us off a little.
But I bet there's one thing
you haven't considered yet.
And that's everyone
who could be voting.
Votes aren't limited
to those watching
here in this auditorium.
There are students
who are watching
in their classrooms.
They can vote instantly
from their devices.
Help me! I'm freaking out
and I don't know what to do!
All right, Shinobun!
It's about time to cut
off the online voitng!
Also, can you please check
the live broadcast?
[SHINOBU] Ah! How am I supposed
to do both things at once?
That's impossible!
Why can't someone
be nice and teach me
how to clone myself?
[NAZUNA]
C'mon, don't cry.
We're going to need everyone
in the broadcast
committee fully functional
to manage the media
during the S1.
[NAZUNA] Trickstar,
I guess I'll have to watch
your performance from
the shadows backstage!
Do you think Akehoshi
and the others
have a chance to win?
They've all been
working so hard.
It's tough to imagine
anyone from Trickstar
giving a mediocre performance.
Besides, you remembered
to elaborate
on those explanations
in the pamphlets,
didn't you, Hajime?
That should help a lot!
So true! Why can't we
all be like Hajime?
There's nothing he
can't do right!
Gross. Don't talk
with your mouth full!
[CROWD]
What?
[HINATA, YUTA] Okay! That was
it, at least from us, for now!
[CROWD]
What?!
[BOTH]
Because you've been so patient,
here comes our main attraction!
[YUTA] This up-and-coming
idol unit always excites
with their cloak of mystery.
These supernovas are
the Revolutionaries of
Yumenosaki Academy!
[HINATA, YUTA] Please welcome
Trickstar to the stage!
[CROWD cheers]
[KURO]
Protect her feelings.
Don't let them go to waste.
[HINATA]
Allow us to introduce you!
He's so calm, chill, and cool:
he's known as The Freezing
Prince. Hidaka Hokuto!
[CROWD cheers]
Boo! There! That's much better--
you were starting to
look a little stiff.
Smile! This is fun, right?
Remember your special training!
I got it!
[HOKUTO]
They're so excited.
I'm definitely feeling
the pressure now.
The next amazing
member is a total
supernova super genius.
Please welcome to the stage,
--Akehoshi Subaru!
--[HOKUTO] Already?
Ya-hoo! Hey there!
Are you all havin' a good time?
[HOKUTO] He always puts his
whole heart into performing,
and his joy is infectious.
That's Akehoshi for you.
Trickstar's first star!
[BOTH] And the next member
we'd like you to meet is...
[YUTA] ...known as the
ever-changing magician.
Isara Mao!
[HOKUTO]
Isara works just as hard
as a student council officer
as he does as a
member of Trickstar.
He's also a fast learner
and can catch up
in a short amount of time
if he misses rehearsals.
Trickstar would've never
become the force
that it is without him.
Last but not least...
is, uh, the glasses guy!
I love the glasses guy!
What's his name? I forgot!
Doesn't really matter--
here he is!
Why is my name the only
one they can't remember?
I'm Yuuki Makoto.
I do stuff, too.
Thanks for coming!
[HOKUTO]
He knows what he's doing.
It helps to have that
comic relief who can make
the audience laugh
and loosen up.
We never worry about
the audience being
too uptight because we have him.
Thank you, Yuuki!
Looks like we've got
a good crowd out there.
That kind of energy
deserves everything
Trickstar has to offer.
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD cheering]
[SUBARU giggles]
Here we go!
This is our song of revolution!
[SUBARU, HOKUTO, MAO, MAKOTO]
"Rebellion Star"!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD cheering]
My goodness! This is so amazing!
The melody is just as
hard as the harmonies,
but they're singing
it perfectly!
Man, why can't you two
ever be in the audience
when I'm performing?
[TOMOYA] I can't believe you're
still stuffing your face!
[STUDENT 04A]
Wow.
[STUDENT 04B]
It's like a starry sky.
[STUDENT 04C] These guys
are actually pretty good.
[STUDENT 04D] They're really
killing it out there.
[STUDENT 04E] I think
they're hot, don't you?
How's the show goin'?
Is your guy crushin' it?
I have no idea what
you're even talking about.
Come on, Izumi. Be real.
Didn't you stay
late the other day
because you were worried
about how nervous
he was getting
during a rehearsal?
Uh, no. What's wrong with you?
[ARASHI] You're not gonna
stay to see how it ends?
[IZUMI]
Why should I?
[ARASHI sighs]
[NAZUNA] We've finished
counting all the votes!
Everyone, please turn your
light sticks off for now!
[ALL panting]
That was so fun!
[CROWD cheers]
And from now on,
we'll keep shining
at this academy, 'cause we
are Yumenoskai idols!
And if you're watching
us from class, thanks!
Mwah! Mwah!
Bye-bye!
[HOKUTO]
Hold on!
--[SUBARU] What?
--The leader of each group
needs to wait. They're
gonna announce the results
and you'll have to represent us.
If we win, you'll have
to accept for us.
Aren't you the leader?
I'm much more comfortable
serving as a right-hand
man or a copilot.
Yeah, I think I'll pass, too.
[SUBARU]
Okay, then how about you, Ukki?
[MAKOTO] No, no, no, no, no!
I can't! Please don't make me!
[YUTA] It doesn't seem like
they're nervous at all.
Oh, I think they've decided.
[HINATA]
I wonder who they picked.
Come on up!
[ANZU]
What?
[sighs]
[NAZUNA] Sorry to keep you guys
in the dark for so long!
I will now announce
the S1 results!
It's so good to see you all,
I'm the broadcast
committee chair
and leader of Ra*bits.
My name is Nito Nazuna!
He managed to sneak
his own unit's name
into the introduction.
Pretty smooth move, kid.
Let us know if you
rigged the votes
so we don't take it personally.
How dare you accuse
me like that!
Even if I had a gwudge
because of what happened
during the S2, I would
still do my job pwoperly!
You better stop makin' fun
of me 'cause I'm little!
Not worth it.
I did my best here.
I'm fine with whatever happens.
Are you guys ready?
The leader of the winning group
will soon be revealed
in a spotlight!
Standby, lighting ops!
When you're ready,
illuminate that
glorious performer
who led their group
to victory tonight!
[REI]
I wonder...
[NAZUNA]
Ta-dah! There she is!
Wow! I didn't see
that one coming!
Which means the winner
of tonight's S1 are...
...that supernova unit...
[HOKUTO, SUBARU, MAO, MAKOTO]
All right!
[NAZUNA]
...Trickstar!
[CROWD cheers]
And by the way...
Here's how the
votes were divided:
The first round came from
our audience here tonight.
The second round
is a student body vote!
No way. When you add
those together...
It's very close.
It looks like we just
barely won by a hair.
So what?
See how many votes we
got from the students?
Pretty awesome to know
that they support us.
That's true.
Especially since we're going
against the student council.
I think we should
consider this win
our first step
toward a revolution!
It's a small move,
but a very big step.
I haven't suffered hardship
like this in a long time.
The bitter taste of defeat.
It's just too much.
[NAZUNA] The student council's
legend of invincibility
has been overturned!
This is crazy!
All of Yumaynosaki
Academy is reeling
from such a huge shock!
[CROWD]
One more song! One more song!
[MAKOTO]
Are they cheering for us?
Don't worry! The winning unit
will be back to
perform one more song
at the end of the night!
But, for now it's
time to celebrate!
Congratulations, Trickstar!
Your hard work is
finally paying off!
Show us what true
winners look like!
There's no way we could
ever be grateful enough!
Every smile you've sent
our way, every cheer.
That support has been a
bright light guiding us here!
Thank you! Thank you, everyone!
[SUBARU]
We love you all!
[knocking]
[door clicks]
I know I'm late
again. I'm sorry.
[TORI growling]
[MAO]
Right...
Isara. Is there a reason
you're standing there?
Better get started;
there's a lot to do.
Uh... You sure it's all right?
This was my fault for being
too confident and comfortable.
And now I've sullied the
prestige of the student council.
Well, being soft is not
gonna solve anything!
We don't want a traitor
for a vice president!
If you need to repent,
I'll punch your face
and hang you in shame
over the school gate!
Young Master, you
need to calm down.
Some nice hot tea
ought to do the trick.
[TORI] I don't wanna
drink tea right now!
Do your paperwork
like I told you!
Fushimi, I'd like
your help, too.
[YUZURU]
Hm?
[KEITO]
I mean, in general.
Honestly, the only reason
I appointed Himemiya
as a student council
officer was so that
I might have the opportunity
to work with you.
[TORI gasps]
What did you just say?!
In fact, I've always wondered
how someone like you could be
content existing this way.
As a subordinate to him.
[TORI growls]
Very much obliged.
What?!
[KEITO]
Please sit down.
I appreciate the courage
and class you've shown
in being here today.
Thanks for that.
It means a lot to me.
I'll win next time.
No matter what.
I suggest you remember
that and pass it on.
[KUNUGI] There is no "next
time." This is showbiz.
[KEITO]
Mr. Kunugi!
I'm gonna be honest
with you, Hasumi.
I'm disappointed.
How could you allow
something like this to happen?
[KEITO]
There's nothing I can say.
You could apologize.
Forgiveness can be
given if you ask.
Doesn't matter how many times
you fall face first in the dirt.
You can get up, put on clean
clothes, and keep walking.
That's quite the gift,
if you think about it.
Want that "next time,"
it's up to you.
He should not speak
to you like that!
Who cares if he's
an advisor? It's rude!
Please, you're making it worse.
There's only one thing
I can do to redeem myself.
I have to win.
It's my duty.
I've been trusted by
the president to maintain
the pure integrity
of Yumenosaki Academy.
And I won't let him down.
[SUBARU]
Found it!
[MAKOTO]
A marble? Is that what it is?
Let me see.
[SUBARU]
Mm-hm! I buried it here.
About a year ago,
before we all met.
I thought I'd told you
about that night.
There's a legend that says
this cherry tree
grants wishes. But...
But it doesn't matter,
that's all in the past now.
Let's go, guys. I'm glad
you're all my friends.
[SUBARU] We'll dash toward
the future together!
Did we actually win that battle?
It's real, right?
It is. It hasn't sunk
in yet for me either.
Things are going
to be so different
at school starting tomorrow.
We're gonna inspire students
to start taking action.
I have no doubt in my mind.
Something wrong?
[gasps]
[EICHI] Well, well, well.
Hello, everyone.
I thoroughly enjoyed
your performance today.
It was so unique.
The passion and sparkles were
almost too much to take!
And what's more... Heh.
I loved watching Keito
lose his mind like that.
Your shine is special.
[EICHI] Not like the reflection
off a glass marble.
Like the moon winking
from behind the stars.
Hello, Trickstar.
Hope to see you around.
I know he's wearing
our school uniform,
but I don't think
I've ever seen him.
[HOKUTO growls]
Hokke?
Can't believe he'd
have the nerve
to show up at a time like this.
It feels like all the joy I
had from our win was stolen.
[MAKOTO, SUBARU]
Hm?
That guy.
He's the reigning top idol
of Yumenosaki Academy
and the leader of "fine,"
the unit that stands
above all other units.
To us, he's the strongest
and worst enemy
we could ever face.
He's the student council
president, the "Emperor."
Tenshouin Eichi!
[ANZU] No one expected the
night to turn out that way.
Nor did they have any idea.
that this particular
meeting would later
shake Trickstar
to its foundation.