[ANNOUNCER A]
Star Television!
[clapping]
[TRICKSTAR, EDEN MEMBERS]
Coming to you live!
The Pre-SS Special,
Trickstar versus Eden!
And a hot discussion!
Keep your eyes on us! We're
the frontrunners in this game!
[SUBARU]
We'll be going till morning!
Wait, how long did you say?
I can't stay in character
without a script until morning.
We're live.
Please keep comments like that
to a whisper, Your Excellency.
Excuse me! Can we cut?
Please edit that last part!
Wait. Like, cut it out?
[ANZU]
Shh!
[ANZU] There were only
a few days left in the year,
and on that day I was helping
out with the production
of the televised SS pre-show.
[ANZU] Question one:
Why did you become idols?
I guess somebody's ready
to begin questioning!
Well, excuse me! [sighs]
I should've arranged to have
more of our own staff here.
Sit down. You're being
a little much right now.
I have to agree with Nagisa!
Yumenosaki Academy's
hosting the SS, aren't they?
So then why would you want
to put their reputation at risk?
This is a battle field,
and we're all here to fight.
Don't you think pretending
to be best friends
and shaking hands is a bit
hypocritical at this point?
Nothing can be gained
from creating conflict.
However, this world is Hell.
Only a handful of
people can survive
without devouring
the flesh of others.
I'm sorry?
[NAGISA] Normally,
one solely talks to God
at a place of worship.
Occasionally, they'll
go out and give to charity,
share some hopeful
thoughts and prayers,
and receive a
few smiles as a reward.
However, here in
modern day Japan,
the only way to
lead that ideal life
of being someone's dream
is to become an idol.
Well, that was my reason.
My father wished it as well.
Do you have any stories
about him? What was he like?
He was quite similar
to your father actually.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
They were more
like father and son.
One could say
they had twin souls.
But by some unexpected twist,
both of them ended up
with opposite fates.
Question is,
will you choose to walk
the same path as your father?
My dad has nothing
to do with this!
He may have been
the initial reason
I wanted to become an idol.
But now there are others.
Since I've been at Yumenosaki,
I have met many who inspire me.
Becoming an idol is
more important to me now
than it ever was before.
I could do this forever with
the kind of friends I've made.
What's that look?
Mind blown? [chuckles]
[EICHI]
Yes. I see.
That's what I'd
expect from Eden.
They seemed used
to this kind of thing.
Not the same at Yumenosaki.
We tend to go down
the concert artist path.
But Eden does better
in terms of media strategy.
Their production
company, CosPro,
is building a campaign
to split the power of
Yumenosaki Academy and
the idol industry in two.
If this contest's outcome
was determined online,
their institutional might
would surely destroy us.
However, the SS is
a live concert event.
And what's more, we'll have
the academy's full support.
I'm counting on Trickstar.
If anyone can bring us
a miracle, it's them.
Speaking of, how are
those guys doing?
Are they out training
for the SS now?
No, they're off today.
[MAKOTO]
I've done everything I can.
There's no reason to stress
about it at this point.
Besides, I need to find a way
to recharge before the match.
She's starting to turn into a
real producer these days.
I'm proud of her.
[MAKOTO gasps]
Hey! What are you doing?
Snatching people's things
is theft, you know!
Wait! You have such a pretty
face, you shouldn't hide it.
Let me take some shots of you.
Come on, give us
a smile. [chuckles]
You're being especially
cheery today,
and it's kinda creeping me out.
So what is it? What's going on?
[IZUMI]
I don't understand.
Do you expect me to be a
grouch when we're out on a date?
I'm having so much
fun just the two of us.
And look! You're even
wearing the scarf I gave you!
Why wouldn't I want
to capture the moment?
You'd complain
if I didn't wear it!
Oh, don't give me that!
I hate how you're always
so shy, Yuu. [chuckles]
That's fine.
Honestly, you can think
whatever you want to, Izumi.
Here. Got you a
Christmas present.
[IZUMI gasps]
Y'know, for the scarf.
--[IZUMI] Whoa, what?
--And to say thank you.
[laughs] I recognize these!
We used them when we
were child models together!
Cosmetics designed for
elementary school boys.
It was really innovative
for its time, wasn't it?
I can't believe they're
still selling these!
You and I have been through
a lot, haven't we, Izumi?
I'm grateful for all
you've done for me.
[scoffs] I can tell
you're being cheeky.
Whatever. Boys who
work hard grow up
to become the treasures
of this world.
Thanks, Izumi.
[RITSU]
Get a room.
No one here needs to
know all of your business.
I'm sorry!
What's with Isara?
He still asleep?
Yeah. Looks like.
He said being busy
helps him relax.
I guess he's feeling
overwhelmed.
Anyway, I decided
to force him to sleep.
How did you
manage to do that?
[RITSU]
You're not really interested.
You're here for another reason.
[MAKOTO]
Oh. Yeah.
What's he talking about?
Hold on. Eden's doing
a concert here today.
Because this is Yumenosaki
Academy's hometown,
they're trying to get as many
people from enemy territory
on their side before
they perform in the SS.
Wow. That's a lot of effort.
Everyone knows
they're number one.
It's strange they'd go that far.
Why should they be complacent?
Just 'cause they're strong?
[RITSU chuckles] Okay, I guess
I'll be the one to carry Maakun.
I mean, we don't want a repeat
of the Summer Live, right?
We'll spy discreetly.
[IBARA] Well. Well, well, well,
who do we have here?
I knew it. It's Trickstar's
very own Yuuki Makoto!
Cameraman, I'm going
to stand next to him.
Follow me and get some shots
and make sure you
get our best angles.
Tch! Just you two?
Oh! Oops!
I'm sorry, cameras are so
traumatic for you, aren't they?
[IBARA laughs]
What's up with this guy?
Somehow he figured out
that we came here to spy,
and now he's trying
to provoke us on camera.
I'm not buying his act.
Hey, I'm an idol, too, ya know!
You don't need to be concerned
about me and cameras.
[IBARA]
I beg your pardon. Forgive me.
Well, as a fellow idol, I hope
you will join me in an alliance.
I have a favor to ask of you.
I'm sure you wouldn't
refuse a special request,
especially on camera.
[HIYORI]
Thank you, everyone!
We're so happy to
have you all here today!
We've had such a good time
and we hope you'll
support us at the SS, too!
[CROWD cheers]
What's going on?
How did we manage
to get roped into
performing here all of a sudden?
Sorry, I guess I fell
for his provocation.
They're trying
to make us look bad
in front of everyone
before the SS.
They have four people,
we only have two.
We don't even have
our outfits with us.
Just then, the magnificent
backup group entered!
Hey, good morning, Ritsu.
Just a minute.
What are you doing
in that outfit?
[RITSU chuckles] We brought
one for you, too, see?
And one for Yuu, as well.
[MAKOTO gasps]
It turns out this mall
sells uniforms. Cool, huh?
[RITSU, IZUMI]
Hurry up and get changed.
[MAKOTO, MAO]
Okay!
Look at that!
We've got surprise guests!
[CROWD cheers]
I really don't care if
they're Eden or oden .
Rampaging in our hometown
is completely over
the top and uncalled for.
Let me handle this for you.
It's the least
I can do to repay you
for taking care
of me every day.
Did you honestly think
backups would be allowed?
What are you scared?
I've heard you're one of
the strongest units there is,
but this is pretty tragic.
If I'm afraid of anything,
it's clueless commoners like you
disrupting such
a professional event.
Are you trying to
work us up or something?
Well, that is
unfortunate because
Trickstar is way more annoying
than you could ever even
hope to be, so, there! Heh!
Damn! What the heck?
That is way too brutal,
even for someone like you!
Let's stop the madness
and start singing.
Otherwise, our audience
is going to fall asleep.
Don't you agree, Nagisa?
[NAGISA]
Mm-hm.
Okay, I guess it's fine.
I will allow them
to join with us.
Trickstar and...
you other guys...
...from some unit
that no one knows about!
That's not true.
You know who we are.
If you don't, we'll show
you that we're real idols
from Yumenosaki Academy, too.
It's my fault that Knights
can't participate in the SS,
but they sure deserve to.
Did you just
mention the Knights?
So I guess that
group still exists.
Wow.
Well, I guess that
makes sense... for you.
You're acting like you know me.
But we didn't talk when
you were at Yumenosaki.
Now you think you know
what makes sense for me?
Hold on. Did you shrink?
You look a lot shorter, Sakuma.
What? Are you mistaking
me for my brother Rei?
How could you possibly
believe I'm him? I'm not.
If so, I'm gonna
be extremely annoyed.
You're wrong if you thought
you were gonna get
a shot with just Yuu!
Awkward.
[MAO laughs]
I'm counting on you, sir!
You got this!
[CROWD cheers]
[SUBARU]
Oh, Dad.
[DAIKICHI whines]
[thud, wood scraping]
[HOKUTO] Wow. I can't
believe it's actually here.
[WATARU]
Oh, my!
You look like you're up to
something interesting, Hokuto!
Not fair to keep all
the excitement to yourself.
No, it's totally fair.
Do me a favor and
be quiet for a second,
I'm trying to think
about something.
[WATARU gasps]
No way. Is that a safe I see?
Looks like it to me.
I have to find
a way to open it up.
Let me do it! These kinds
of things are my specialty!
Oh! How very complex
and mysterious
with the countless gears
and nested boxes all over.
Whoever had the honor of making
this was quite the monomaniac.
Don't talk about my dad
like that, Wataru.
[gasps] Are you saying
you know who made this?
Yeah, my dad made it.
[WATARU] Naturally, I have
to ask where you found it?
[HOKUTO]
It was on campus.
I heard that he hid it
somewhere before he graduated.
So I asked him where
it was, then I dug it out.
[WATARU]
What?!
Why didn't you invite me
to help with the digging?
I don't know. I didn't
give it that much thought.
Bless your heart.
You're not very good at
using others, are you, dear?
It must be the way
you were raised.
What are you saying?
That reminds me of something
I forgot to tell
you the other day.
[HOKUTO]
So tell me.
You're a thoroughbred
of the entertainment business.
You were born into perfection.
But that comes with some
rather harsh realities.
Despite that, you're a human.
So you're still
going to make mistakes.
But it's different for you.
You've set high expectations,
so you'll face more ridicule.
I wanted to help
you gain the strength
needed to endure that life.
Meaning what?
[WATARU] That's the reason
I had you come onstage with me--
onto that tortuous
hell of a stage.
[WATARU] I had so much
I wanted to teach you.
But our relationship could never
truly be defined as
teacher and student.
We were barely comfortable
enough to chat once in a while.
But just those few moments
brought so much joy,
so it wasn't entirely for you.
Now, having you taste tragedy
that people rarely get
a chance to experience--
that was for no one
else's benefit but yours.
I see.
Well, we're about
to go up against Eden,
our greatest opponent,
and, apparently, there's
a schemer among them now.
So I guess that experience
might come in handy.
Thank you, Club President.
You're welcome.
Now do your best at the SS.
Just like your namesake--
be the North Star and point
others who stray off their path
in the right direction.
Right. Of course I will.
That's why my parents
gave me this name.
--[clicking]
--[WATARU] Ooh! Color me happy!
I unlocked it!
[HOKUTO gasps]
Amazing. No telling
what treasures we'll find!
Know what would be so cool?
If there were some old journals
of your dad's with
lots of juicy gossip.
Yeah, right. Not funny. Open it.
[WATARU gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[HOKUTO]
Is that...?
[CROWD cheering]
[ANZU]
And then,
just like that, the day
of the SS had snuck up on us.
What a great way
to open the show!
That was Eden!
We'll see you
all again very soon!
Please enjoy the rest of your
time here at the Winter Live.
[SUBARU] Aw, man! The opening
ceremonies were amazing!
[SUBARU grunts]
Know what's weird?
After they got
finished with their act,
Eden referred to the
SS as the Winter Live.
[MAO]
CosPro probably told them to.
Maybe so it would match with
Summer Live and Autumn Live.
Sounds like they're trying to
take ownership of the concert,
so they can incorporate
it into their events.
Wow. I think it's better as SS,
since that's what Yumenosaki's
been calling it for years.
[HOKUTO] Truth is,
Eden will probably win.
If they do, then CosPro
will officially take over
the biggest national idol event
even though it was established
by Yumenosaki Academy.
--[phone buzzes]
--[SUBARU] Mm?
Barry's messaging me.
He says he has something to tell
me, but it has to be in private.
That dude's so shady!
[MAKOTO]
Be careful.
We just barely got
through the mall concert,
and we couldn't have done it
without Izumi and Ritsu.
You don't have
to go talk to him.
All you'll be doing is
helping him out with his plan.
I agree. It sounds like a trap.
Roger.
[MAN A, MAN B]
Hm...
[HIYORI]
What's this?
You're getting tired
a lot faster than usual.
Not very Hiyori.
Believe me, I know it's not.
I've been in love with the
SS ever since I was a kid,
so I'm feeling the pressure.
I get kind of emotional
thinking about it,
since it was so
important to my dad.
[HIYORI chuckles]
There, there.
All right, you're suffocating
me. I don't like this.
Let me go, already.
In this cruel world, you should
be grateful for my kindness.
My goodness, you two
get along well, don't you?
Oh? If you're feeling
a little jealous,
I'll hug you, too, Nagisa.
I want you to be there for Jun,
just like you were there
for me many years ago.
Wait a minute, you always
act like you don't remember
our past together!
Okay, okay!
As the oldest one here,
I have to say
I love all of you very much
and that means forever and ever!
[NAGISA] Hm? What's with
the long face, Ibara?
[gasps] Nothing.
Feeling left out?
Come here. Let us
shower you with affection.
No thanks, I'll refrain.
What you don't understand is
I don't have the right
to accept human joy,
but you'll be the first
to know if that changes.
No right?
It's my bloodline.
I'm related to a magnate
who once ruled over
the entertainment business.
It's not publicized,
but I'm his direct descendant.
Are you talking about my father?
Yes, he wanted me to
call him Mr. Godfather,
or something like that,
and out of respect, that's the
way I've always referred to him.
But in my mind, he was much
more like a great-grandfather.
[IBARA] My parents
were probably deep in debt,
and they abandoned
me on the street one day
when I was just a baby.
Because of that,
I spent my hellish
childhood in an orphanage.
When the aforementioned
Mr. Godfather passed away,
they found his will,
and I received a part
of his inheritance,
which proved to be quite
beneficial later on.
[IBARA] What I'm saying is,
that I became an idol
simply because it's the
best way to successfully
utilize the company and the
connections that I inherited.
[NAGISA grunts]
[IBARA]
Which is another reason...
No matter what happens,
we absolutely cannot
fail this Winter Live!
If we win this,
it'll also solidify
Eden's position in CosPro!
I know, you're right.
We're with you.
So is that why you're taking
special precautions
against Trickstar?
Yes. They're not quite our
greatest enemies, of course,
but they should be
prepared for battle.
You know, in case we end up
having to deploy a weapon
with immense destructive force.
[sighs]
And, to be perfectly honest,
I'm praying that
we won't have to
resort to those
kinds of measures.
I would've liked
to talk with Subaru.
I would have asked
him to withdraw.
[IBARA] But alas,
no matter how we struggle,
we won't be able to
stop it from getting bloody.
[ANZU] Meanwhile, downtown,
the SS prelims were being held.
All the students were doing what
they could to help the staff.
They were getting
people fired up
by advertising
Trickstar's competition.
When visitors from
different parts of the country
would come in for the show,
they'd be sure to
let them know that
they were in Yumenosaki
Academy's hometown.
Tenshouin and
Hidaka's dad became
part of the SS's
executive committee.
They made sure everything
ran as smoothly as possible.
[ANZU] Trickstar was
also doing their best
to reward everybody's
support with their hard work.
Finally!
[KUNUGI]
And now for the results.
The last unit to make
it to the finals is...
[KUNUGI, SAGAMI]
...Trickstar!
[CROWD cheering]
[SUBARU]
These are awesome!
So sparkly! I love them!
Thank you so much, Anzu.
They kinda remind me of
the ones we had for the DDD.
Did you pull an all-nighter?
Oh, no. I had some help.
Kiryu and Itsuki
were an awesome team.
I slept quite well
last night. [gasps]
It's almost time, you guys!
Yeah! Let's go!
[ALL] Turn expectations to hope!
Let's make a breakthrough!
Feel the...
...reason...
...why we're...
...here right now!
[ALL]
To the future!
Good to see you
again, Trickstar.
It looks like you're ready.
Now, to the stage!
Proceed through the
Yumenosaki passageway!
[TRICKSTAR MEMBERS]
Right!
[SUBARU]
My dad was like the sun to me.
After he passed away,
my heart became frozen.
But before I knew it,
I was surrounded by warmth
from these bright stars.
I'm not alone anymore!
And they were all
with me when I got here!
[CROWD cheering]
Oh, wow!
Feels so unreal!
This is the biggest idol event
in the nation, and we made it!
[SUBARU gasps]
[giggles]
[SUBARU]
Mom... Daikichi...
Dad, are you
watching from Heaven?
I did it. I'm an idol!
Ah... What the...?
Maybe it's... um,
part of the concert?
Hey, what's going on out there?
Huh?
[SUBARU gasps]
[HOKUTO] Akehoshi?
Do you know what's happening?
[MAKOTO]
What? Criminal?
[MAO]
Removed from the idol industry?
Does that say Akehoshi?
[SUBARU gasps]