[CROWD murmuring]
[SAGAMI]
Attention, please.
The executive committee
is currently deliberating.
[KUNUGI] We're sorry
for the inconvenience.
Thank you for your patience.
[CHIAKI grunts]
[CROWD cheering]
[gasps]
[SUBARU gasps]
[footsteps]
How are you
holding up, Akehoshi?
Hidaka!
Who's behind it? Do they know?
No, not yet.
All we know for sure is that
someone hijacked the network.
And their sole motive
was to air that footage.
[MAKOTO] They wanted to expose
Akehoshi's dad's criminal past.
Though the accusations
were never really proven.
And as if that
wasn't bad enough,
it implies that
Akehoshi's guilty, too,
just for knowing him.
[MAO]
Subaru.
Your hands are freezing, buddy.
Lemme warm them up for you.
Think our friend
needs some love!
--[MAKOTO] Uh, sure.
--[HOKUTO] Right.
We've got your back.
Listen, guys. I'm...
You're trembling, buddy.
You don't have to talk.
Stay calm, guys.
Let's take some deep breaths.
--Yeah, that's a good idea.
--Okay.
Just focus on
breathing in and then out.
Time it to the
rhythm of your hearts.
One, two, three.
[ALL inhale, exhale]
[SUBARU]
Sorry.
I never meant to drag
you guys into this.
[HOKUTO]
You didn't.
[MAKOTO]
Hm. Listen, Hidaka?
[HOKUTO]
Mm?
Your dad and Subaru's,
they were pretty good friends
back in the day, weren't they?
What are you getting at?
Look, we're your friends,
so you can be honest.
Is there any truth to
those defamatory statements?
Makoto, don't!
[MAKOTO]
We need to know the truth...
...to protect him.
That's the only
reason I'm asking.
[SUBARU] It's okay.
I'll tell you what I know.
I can't say for sure what kind
of person my dad really was.
But to me, he sparkled
like a shooting star.
I thought he could do no wrong.
You could say he was my idol.
But then...
[SUBARU]
Who's a good boy, Daikichi?
[SUBARU] ...it was
just like any other day.
I was waiting
for him to get home.
Then I heard my dad's name
on the television.
[SUBARU]
I was shocked.
The reporter said... that
someone had died onstage...
...and my dad had killed them.
[MAKOTO, HOKUTO, MAO gasp]
[MAKOTO] Hold on,
he murdered someone onstage?
It wasn't murder,
just an accident.
Apparently, a rogue fan
climbed up on the stage.
[thud]
[CROWD yelling]
[HOKUTO] Things got out
of hand, and the fan fell off.
It was a really bad fall,
and they died in the end.
But no one who was
there thought that
Akehoshi's dad had pushed them.
--[thud]
--[gasps]
[SUBARU] Still, that was the
beginning of the end for him.
Dad wasn't charged with murder,
but the investigation turned
up plenty of other things.
Eventually,
he was arrested again.
Illegal contributions, violence
towards his colleagues...
Evidence just kept surfacing.
[SUBARU] They started calling
him the worst idol in history.
I had to hear that
about my own father.
The name Akehoshi became
synonymous with crime.
And, as for me and mom, we were
pariahs shunned by society.
Dad never got the chance
to vindicate himself either.
He passed away in jail.
That's when I decided
I would go to Yumenosaki Academy
and become an idol
just like my dad.
[SUBARU]
I wanted to give the world
something sparkling
and precious.
Something good to hold on to.
That was all my dad wanted...
and it became my dream, too!
But after this,
I'm afraid of going onstage.
Anyone would be! If my
parents had been disgraced,
I wouldn't be able to keep it
together! I'd be a total wreck!
But-- [gasps]
Look at me.
All of us are in
this fight together!
You will never stand alone.
We'll be at your side!
Yeah, that's right!
I mean, I'm afraid
of being on camera,
but with you guys supporting me,
I'm able to do it!
Ukki...
And look at me.
Back in middle school,
people suggested
that I might make
a good idol, and I listened.
So I figured
I'd try my luck here.
Plus, it would
give me the chance
to hang out with Ritsu more.
But now I'm kinda relieved
to just be an average guy.
And if you're scared to
be onstage, don't worry.
You can count on me,
'cause I'll be the flashlight
lighting your path to stardom!
[SUBARU chuckles]
That means a lot, Sally.
Pardon me, gents!
What's your problem, Akehoshi?
Didn't I tell you to call
on us if you needed help?
I don't know what
jerk did this to you,
but they're a no-good,
dirty, cheater!
They tried to drag your
name through the dirt,
but they won't get away with it!
Yeah, this kind
of thing makes me sick.
[KANATA] Evil never prospers,
not on my watch, anyway!
Hey, Morisawa.
I need to ask a favor.
Do you think Ryuseitai could
keep Akehoshi company for now?
[CHIAKI]
Hmm?
[MAO]
So, Hokuto, what's the plan?
I'm gonna go visit Eden.
Really? Do you
think they did this?
Please don't beat them up.
No way. You don't really think
they're to blame here, do you?
[HOKUTO grunts]
[MAO]
Then, who is?
We don't know yet,
but I don't think it's Eden--
that video went too far.
[HOKUTO] I don't think
they did it either.
For one thing,
as Isara and Anzu discovered
during the Autumn Live,
things are pretty complicated
on Eden's end, too.
That said, if they really
see themselves as idols,
they may help us
fight our common enemy.
[IBARA groans]
And they've gone and done
it again. Those idiots.
[HOKUTO]
And what's more,
we might be able
to turn the tables.
We just have to use
what I gave Anzu.
[MAO]
Huh? What'd you give her?
[EICHI] So... you plan
to open Pandora's box.
With this, we can
root out the corruption
that's pervaded our
industry for years.
Where are the others?
As far as I know, they're
talking to Eden as we speak.
Very well. I'll take
action immediately.
Listen, if there's
anything at all I can do...
[EICHI]
This is my responsibility.
And regardless...
You have more important
things to do, don't you?
[ANZU gasps]
Sakuma, sir!
Well, shouldn't you
be consoling Trickstar
right now in
their time of crisis?
I do believe I warned you during
the Summer Live. [chuckles]
[ANZU]
Yes, sir!
Have the SS
competitions resumed?
They're about to.
Thank you for all
the help. I'm grateful.
No sweat. This was
the least I could do.
It would be a disaster
if the audience left.
We have to prevent
that at all costs.
[KOGA]
All right!
We feel those nervous vibes,
but we'll blow them away.
As you may know,
this event has a long history,
and we have to protect it!
Hey there, what's up?
It's kinda cold.
Why don't we get this crowd
movin' and warm the place up?
All right, the event
will continue as planned.
The main competitions
will be starting up soon!
I shall guide you
with all haste.
Let us charge forth
and conquer the enemy!
[OPERATOR A]
We just need someone
to give us instructions--
[MAO] Sorry. I would,
but my hands are full.
Sorry for the delay!
[MAO]
Anzu!
[MAO, MAKOTO, HOKUTO]
Mm!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANZU]
The main competitions for the SS
proved tougher than
they'd ever been before.
[ANZU] Akehoshi hadn't
fully recovered yet,
but everyone supported
him without question.
[SUBARU gasping]
Well, we managed it.
We made it through
the first match.
Excellent work.
Akehoshi, here.
[MAO]
Oh, no!
My outfit!
Well, this isn't good.
Guess we must've
danced too hard.
I'll sew them up!
[KURO]
You don't need to.
We'll have those jackets
lookin' good as new in no time.
[MAO]
You guys are here?
My, you really are
troublesome, aren't you?
--Kagehira.
--I hear ya.
Okay, you just sit tight, buddy.
Thanks a bunch.
[KUNUGI]
Are you folks ready?
The unit's moving on
to the finals are...
[SAGAMI]
...Eden and Trickstar!
[CROWD cheering]
[RYUSEITAI MEMBERS]
All right, Trickstar!
[BOTH] Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
So it begins.
Oh, yeah! Only one more
for the win now, boys!
Oh, no.
I can already feel myself
starting to tear up.
But, the thing is,
the problem lies ahead.
And they haven't
even mentioned it yet--
the controversial video.
Now that they're in the final,
they have to address it
somehow, don't you agree?
Poor Akehoshi.
[JUN grunting]
Jun, please, will you
at least try to calm down?
Goddamn! I feel like
the entertainment industry's
always gonna be
rotten to the core.
Why has nothing
changed in all this time?
All right, Jun, that's enough.
Mind your manners.
Saegusa, is everything
square and ready to go?
Oh. I'll leave that
to your imagination.
We'll betray you
when it comes down to it.
So don't go thinking we're your
best friends all of a sudden.
Ibara, enjoying yourself?
[IBARA gasps]
[IBARA] Ehem. Well currently,
we have mutual interests,
so I'll tolerate this.
Let us now commence
our joint operation!
We'll publicly denounce
CosPro's top brass
for framing one of their idols.
I'm ashamed to say it,
but it was pure
mismanagement on our part.
Arrogant simpletons.
Did they think they'd
get away with this?
Bringing light to
a high-profile scandal--
one that our predecessors took
such pains to make go away?
Yeah, really now.
Very bad Hiyori.
To save the future
of entertainment,
we will thwart this
evil scheme together.
Wow, Barry, you love
being an idol.
To be quite honest,
I could take it or leave it.
I just happen to have a pet
peeve about things like this.
It drives me crazy.
I'm grateful for the chance to
catch those buffoons off-guard.
[CROWD cheering]
I trust that I have
all of your attention!
Are you ready for
something out of this world?
Welcome to a lawless
paradise forsaken by God.
You've entered the
capital of pleasures--
a place bursting with desire.
Abandon your faith,
and fall with us into a decadent
realm of unbound depravity!
[IBARA, CROWD]
Attack! Conquer! Destroy!
[laughs]
[CROWD cheers]
[JUN]
Take that!
From now on, when people
say the name Sazanami,
they'll be calling out to me!
Do your best, Sazanami.
[HIYORI giggles] At this rate,
we will slowly but surely
spread smiles and love
to the ends of the earth.
Once upon a time,
that was Eichi and I's goal.
The ideal Hiyori!
[NAGISA] Everybody is smiling.
Seems like they're having fun.
Watching them makes something
warm start to grow in my heart.
[IBARA]
Huh...
What an odd sensation,
to be doing something good.
I feel more natural
playing the villain. Hm.
Yuzuru...
...are you laughing
at the sight of me now?
Or do you think me admirable?
He's the same as ever.
Nothing new here.
[phone buzzes]
[TORI]
Hey, there.
Do you, like, know
that guy or something?
Because I've never heard of him.
Uh... Master...
[TORI]
Never mind.
Just know that if you ever do
feel like talking about him,
I'll be ready to listen.
Yeah. It's my job
as your master.
Thanks.
This is just amazing!
Now is hardly the time
to be chatting, my friends!
Look! Up there!
[CROWD murmuring]
[SUBARU panting]
Thank you. I'll... do my best.
[ANZU gasps]
[MAKOTO gasps]
[MAKOTO]
I'll cover you, Akehoshi.
Way to go, Yuu! Super manly!
And check out my Maakun.
He's pretty manly himself.
Here, your mic!
Thank you.
Remember to take deep breaths!
[SUBARU gasping]
[inhales, exhales]
Hello.
My name is Subaru Akehoshi.
--[AUDIENCE A] Subaru?
--[AUDIENCE B] It's him!
[SUBARU] I'm sorry
for what happened today.
But, please, I hope you'll
be willing to hear me out.
My dad... he was framed.
The allegations are
false. I can prove it.
My friend's father secretly kept
several documents from the time.
They'll clear my dad's name.
Therefore, I plan
to make them public.
In order to prevent foul play,
the Tenshouin Financial Group
and the Tomoe Foundation,
among others, have approached
the police pre-emptively.
Everybody, freeze!
No one make a move.
[SUBARU]
The whole truth will be
brought to light
in the New Year.
That's right, your colleagues
are quite capable, Yuzuru...
[SUBARU] But still, I don't
know how it will all turn out.
And even if my father is
cleared of all charges,
I know nothing will
bring him back.
It's all just so heartbreaking.
He's been struggling
with this all along,
and I never had a clue.
Yeah. You still have
a lot to learn. We all do.
To tell the truth,
my father has always
been a hero to me.
I'm so happy!
I want to sing and
bring sparkling smiles
to people everywhere.
For all these years
that's what I've lived for!
I met some wonderful friends,
and made it here
to the SS stage.
Honestly, I don't have
a single thing to hide.
I don't have anything
to be ashamed of!
And, so
if you'll accept it, I'd like to
offer you a song from my heart!
[footsteps]
[HOKUTO]
Akehoshi!
[MAO]
Subaru!
[MAKOTO]
Akehoshi!
[gasps]
Come on, now.
Time to hold your head high.
That's right!
[SUBARU gasps]
[CROWD clapping, cheering]
[RA*BITS MEMBERS]
Yahoo!
--[MITSURU] Wonderful!
--[SORA] Wow!
It's so glorious!
All the colors!
Well done. Truly.
His future is bright.
He really tapped
into something big.
I agree. He'll be able
to change everything now!
Thanks for showing
us all such beauty!
It's what the world needs!
Bless this audience for
allowing idols to shine together
like we knew we could!
[GROUP]
Yeah!
Thank you so much. Truly!
Subaru!
--[HOKUTO] It worked!
--[MAKOTO] Akehoshi!
[SUBARU giggles]
[ALL]
We appreciate all of our fans!
[SUBARU]
Now lend us your ears
for the miracle that
will shape the future!
[TRICKSTAR MEMBERS]
"Infinite Star"!
[CROWD cheers]
[NAGISA gasps]
[NAGISA]
I remember.
Back then, when I was a child,
he stretched out his hand to
infinite sparkling lights.
And both my father and I,
we loved him deeply.
We looked up to him.
[NAGISA]
A lot of people said my father
was a heartless tyrant,
but I knew better.
He had his own way of loving.
[NAGISA]
I understand now.
We share a goal--
to bring people joy
through our music.
That's why we sing--
to lessen this world's
sorrow as much as we can.
[KUNUGI]
The results are in
for the SS final match.
[NAGISA]
Subaru.
There may be some who laugh,
mock your father's path,
and say that he
was a foolish man.
But not me.
I think he made
an admirable choice.
[SUBARU]
Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
You've worked so hard.
You've earned this.
[KUNUGI]
The winner is...
[SAGAMI]
...Trickstar!
--[TRICKSTAR MEMBERS gasp]
--[CROWD cheering]
I- Wait! Did we win?
Whoa! Get a hold
of yourself, leader!
We did it!
Yes! We sure did! We really won!
[SUBARU chuckles]
Thanks, Sally, Ukki, and Hokke!
Woo-hoo!
And thanks to every one of you!
Also, thanks to our producer!
[ALL]
Thanks for everything, Anzu!
[CROWD]
Way to go!
[HIYORI] Well, I guess we
should congratulate them, huh?
Yep! Goddamn!
Well, congratulations!
Aw, it's too bad,
don't you think, Ibara?
I think I'm okay with it.
But we'll beat you next
time for sure, Trickstar,
so watch your backs!
I salute!
[CROWD]
Trickstar!
And now the winners
get the privilege
of performing an encore!
But first, how 'bout
some love for the audience?
[HOKUTO, MAO, MAKOTO]
Subaru!
[SUBARU]
Mm. I hope everyone here knows
that you made this the happiest
moment of my whole life!
I'm smiling so much I don't
even know if I can sing to you!
So help us out and sing along!
Let's all sing
together as an ensemble!
And may our voices be heard
around the world forever!
[ALL]
Ensemble Stars!