[ANZU]
It was a remarkably clear day,
especially for the rainy season,
when something sprang
up out of the blue.
[EICHI]
Hello there, transfer student.
Uh.
So RYUSETAI's show
the other day.
Quite impressive.
[ANZU]
Oh, thanks so much.
[EICHI] I was wondering
if I could ask for a favor.
Uh, sure.
Well, a producer's job
entails much more
than just looking after
idols and their units.
They have to plan and oversee
events sometimes, too.
Don't you agree?
Yeah, absolutely.
[EICHI] Well, that
brings us to my request.
Would you be in charge
of running the next DreFes?
Uh...
What?!
[ANZU]
A DreFes.
And it's an S1 at that.
I don't even know
where to start!
[HAJIME] Isn't this the
perfect day for doing laundry?
[TOMOYA]
Yeah, it's been raining nonstop,
so the clothes were
really piling up.
I'm sorry.
I know you don't want to spend
this gorgeous day
hanging clothes.
Oh, no worries.
Mitsuru likes
to run in the rain.
His clothes get dirty fast.
He doesn't seem like the type
to let a little rain get
in the way of his fun.
This is the best
day ever! [laughing]
[NAZUNA muffled grunting]
I made a mistake!
--[NAZUNA] Someone help me!
--I got ya, friend!
Here I come to the rescue!
Stop wiggling.
You're making it worse.
Jeez.
That's what happens when a tiny
person hangs up a huge sheet.
[NAZUNA]
You shut your mouth!
[KAORU] Do you guys have
to be so loud? Seriously.
[HAJIME, TOMOYA, MITSURU]
Huh?
[KAORU] I'm trying to have
a little sun nap over here,
so hush up.
[NAZUNA]
Is that Kaoruchin?
Don't just sit there.
Come help me!
[KAORU]
Oh, fine.
[gasps, sighs]
Fresh air never
tasted so delicious.
You shorties always
seem to be having fun.
Don't you call me shorty!
[HAJIME]
Uh...
Oh. I know this one
may look a little scary,
but he's not a bad guy.
Hey, Kaoruchin!
Since you're free,
we need your help!
Nah, as a rule,
I only help girls.
Okay, suit yourself.
I'll tell the whole
school how you hit on me
'cause you thought I was a girl.
Eh! Man, am I ever gonna
live that one down?
[ANZU]
'Scuse me.
[ALL]
Hmm?
[NAZUNA]
Anzu.
Oh. I assume you're
here to see me?
Uh, sorry, no.
This just fell off
the clothesline.
Huh? Is that...?
Ah, man, now it's dirty again!
Thanks for giving it back.
[ANZU]
'Course. Well, see you later.
Oh. Hey, wait up. I'll join.
Wait. That's right!
I wanted to ask,
what would you all want
the ideal DreFes to be like?
What do you mean?
Huh. That's a good question.
Easy. I'd want an enormous stage
so I can run as much as
I want when I get the zoomies!
I'd like for it to be
focused on beautiful singing.
And I'd really
appreciate a point system
that didn't put new units at
such a massive disadvantage.
We know units that have
been around the longest
are gonna have some natural
advantages over new ones.
But in the DDD, it's rough,
since you're knocked out
of the running after
your first loss.
Why are you asking about that?
Are you writing
a report or something?
No, as a matter of fact,
I've just been put
in charge of the next S1.
[ALL]
What?!
[ANZU]
First of all.
I need to decide how
big this event should be,
then I'll pick a theme
and put together a budget.
[KAORU]
Hey, Anzu?
Once that's done,
I'll start designing
and constructing the stage.
Oh, and I also
can't forget about--
Is anyone home?
[ANZU gasps]
Yeah? What is it?
I think you need to delegate
some responsibilities.
Like, enlist help?
Yup. You need a few
energetic assistants
who won't say no to
doing your dirty work.
[ADONIS panting]
[SOUMA panting]
Well played. Just like I
imagined, I'm no match for you.
And to add insult to injury,
you're not even
winded right now.
I am. I'm just a whole lot
better at concealing it.
Here. It's important
to stay hydrated.
You're too kind.
Hits the spot.
[KAORU]
Hey, guys!
Huh?
Hope you guys aren't
working too hard.
[ADONIS] Oh, look.
It's Anzu... and Hakaze.
This is no place for
weaklings like you,
marine life club disgrace!
How dare you show
your face around here?
Oh, Souma, still not showing
respect to your elders?
Can't say I'm surprised.
However, Otsukare knows
how the hierarchy works.
Um, Hakaze, my name isn't
Otsukare. It's Otogari.
We're in the same unit,
so I'd appreciate it
if you'd remember that.
Anyway, did you need something?
[SOUMA] You okay?
Did this ruffian abduct you?
Actually, I was about
to ask if she'd like--
--Not a chance, buddy.
--[KAORU chuckles]
Can I tell you guys something?
--[SOUMA] What?!
--[ADONIS] What did you say?!
Okay, what is this?
Ya tryin' to take over
my dojo or something?
Sure, that's it.
No, but here's the thing--
we are definitely going to need
an exclusive
outfit for a DreFes.
Exactly. We decided
to seek your counsel
before doing
anything, Sir Kiryu.
Wait, back up.
I'm not actually following yet.
[ANZU]
I'll cut to the chase then.
[KURO]
What?
[KEITO]
What in the world are you up to?
[EICHI chuckles]
She's in league with Trickstar,
who dared bare its teeth
to the student council.
So I gave her a project
that I knew would crush her.
Is that what you
thought I'd say?
Not that extreme, but yes.
[EICHI] That girl is this
Academy's one and only producer.
So if she keeps getting better,
then everyone will benefit.
[knocking]
[SOUMA]
Pardon me. Sir Hasumi?
What now?
--[SOUMA] May I come in?
--[EICHI] She's already begun.
Impressive.
[knocking]
I'll leave the rest to you.
[door opens]
A moment, please.
What is it, Kanzaki?
[SOUMA] Lady Anzu
requests your instruction.
It's in regard to DreFes
planning and management.
If I'm going to
create a new DreFes,
I need to know as much
information as possible
about all the past events.
Anzu?
Isara.
What's going on?
[KEITO]
Perfect timing, Isara.
Would you help Anzu carry
these documents to the library?
That way she can peruse
them to her heart's content.
[MAO gasps]
[MAO]
There ya go.
That's the last of 'em, right?
Sure is.
This is such
a pleasant surprise.
I can't believe you're
planning the next Drefes.
I know, it's crazy.
Well, let me know
if you need anything.
I'd be happy to help.
And not just me.
All of Trickstar's here for you.
We're just a call away.
Aw, thanks!
It would seem that
our work here is done.
For the time being at least.
She needs to brainstorm
about it on her own.
If there's any heavy lifting,
you guys can help her with it.
And since I'm the one who
enlisted you as assistants,
I'll score major
points with her too.
You're a scoundrel,
you know that?!
[ANZU]
I see.
Before the current
Drefes ranking system,
they did it in
a number of other ways.
Huh.
[NATSUME]
You worried about something?
Hey, kitten.
Doesn't the moon
look beautiful tonight?
[ANZU]
Uhh...
[NATSUME chuckles]
I know what you're thinking.
"The moon isn't even out yet."
But why not indulge in a flight
of fancy every now and then?
True beauty comes not from
the eyes, but from the mind.
Right.
[NATSUME] I get the feeling
you might not remember me.
I am one of your
classmates, you know.
[inaudible]
Oh, that's right,
your name's Sakasaki.
You're the one who ditched
when we were both on
class duty the other day.
Embarrassing.
Wish you remembered me
for something better.
Well, anyway, as
I'm a skilled magician,
I can help assuage
all your anxieties...
...using my magic.
Your magic?
[NATSUME] That's what I said.
But only on one condition.
[gasps]
I want you to agree
to go out with me.
[ALL panting]
Yeah! That was perfect.
Right, kitten?
[SORA]
Woo-hoo!
Well, I personally think
we looked super cool
that time around!
[TSUMUGI]
You totally nailed the lighting
with just a few
minutes of practice.
That was amazing!
Thanks so much for doing this!
Oh, it's nothing, really.
I'm happy to help!
[TSUMUGI]
Because of you,
we're ready to perform
for the B1 today.
I was scared we
wouldn't make it!
To say that I panicked when
the original lighting person
canceled at the last minute
would be an understatement!
He was freaking out.
But because you were
willing to help Master,
everything is
gonna work out now!
Exactly.
You must've been
pretty surprised
when Natsume asked
you out, right?
What a dork.
I sure was.
I didn't ask her out.
Just if she'd come
with me for the day.
There's no ulterior motive.
Of course there isn't.
But you better stay
for class duty next time.
I'm never gonna live
that one down, am I?
I'm curious, why me?
For concerts at the academy,
shouldn't you ask the student
council or broadcast committee?
The B1's an unofficial
free-for-all competition.
We aren't technically supposed
to ask the school for help.
We were trying to
think of a replacement
and then I remembered
that you helped out
with RYUSEITAI's
hero show recently.
But he was worried that you
might not agree to help,
even if we asked.
I told him that you might,
but he didn't believe me.
--Heh.
--But we're fine now!
At the end of the day,
you were worrying for nothing!
Yeah.
[NATSUME]
You really were, Tsumugi.
In the chaotic world we live in,
being anxious about the future
is a sign of intelligence,
but when it prevents you
from living your life,
it's dysfunctional.
In other words,
you're kinda useless.
That's why you decided
to ask Anzu yourself.
Because you knew I couldn't
bring myself to do it.
He may be a little weirdo,
but he's our little weirdo!
[NATSUME grunts]
Ugh! What self-respecting
magician punches somebody
instead of casting
a hex on them?
I would, but, for some reason,
you seem to be immune to magic.
[SORA]
Woo-hoo!
The concert is about to begin.
We better head to
the dressing room!
We put a lot of effort
into publicity.
So I'm sure we'll
have an audience.
[EICHI] Yes. I have
a question regarding that.
[ALL]
Huh?
[TSUMUGI]
Eichi?
[EICHI]
Well, Tsumugi,
care to tell me
what this is about?
For some odd reason,
it shows that fine is also
performing at the B1 today.
Well, um, that's
actually 'cause...
He asked for a tiny, little
favor from an old pal, you see.
Wataru.
I have a weak spot for
him when he looks at me
and begs with those
big ol' puppy dog eyes.
I am like a big brother
to him, after all. [laughs]
Don't go thinking that
you've paid your debt now.
You're still very
much on the hook.
I haven't forgiven you
yet for joining fine,
and I'm still not sure if
I ever will, Big Brother Wataru.
[WATARU]
Mm-hm, mm-mm.
[EICHI]
Oh, I see what this is.
You want to take
Wataru for yourself.
Best of luck.
Just listen to yourself.
You're talking as if you
actually believe that
Big Brother Wataru
belongs to you.
He isn't wrong.
The fact of it is that
I belong to one and all,
for I am everyone's
Wataru Hibiki.
Eichi. It's our first B1.
Switch has never performed for
the school in this way before.
So I was thinking
that fine could help
brighten up our performance.
That's right.
Even though you
forfeited the DDD,
you retain your
reputation as the top unit.
There's no better unit
to support us in this.
So we would love for you
to give us your blessing.
And what exactly would
compel me to do such a thing?
[TSUMUGI]
I can think of one good reason
off the top of my head.
Since I'm part of the
reason that fine exists,
it's only natural that the group
would want to support me now.
At any rate, this is my plan.
So if you're dissatisfied,
you can direct your
complaints to me.
I've never been
dissatisfied with you.
Though I will say this.
If you're trying to
impress people tonight,
you should cut all
that hair off your neck.
And those glasses
do you no favors.
Do you always have
to be so critical?
[ANZU giggles]
Transfer student, do you have
time to be involved with this?
I assumed that you'd be focused
solely on writing your proposal.
I, uh...
Never mind.
Wataru, are Tori
and Yuzuru here, too?
Indeed, they're already changing
in the dressing room
just over there.
Very well.
Out of respect for our past,
I'll go with your plan.
[laughs] Thank you very much!
But we won't try to
tone ourselves down
to make you look good.
So if we steal the show
from you, don't blame me.
[door opens, closes]
All right, let's
begin the magic ritual.
The lonely dictator recovers
all the accoutrements
he forfeited in the past.
And this time,
he'll make the flowers of
love bloom around the world!
--[TSUMUGI] Nicely done!
--[SORA] Oh wow!
Now, let's go!
[CROWD cheers]
Sorry for dragging you into
such a complicated situation.
[ANZU]
Huh?
So much has happened.
Eichi, Natsume, and I
have quite the history.
Things got messy. We fought,
hurt each other,
almost gave up at one point.
But, now, here we are.
Sometimes I can't believe it.
[CROWD cheers]
[panting]
Thank you!
And next up, my friend,
who helped me to create fine,
Aoba Tsumugi, singing
from his new perch.
Here's Switch.
[CROWD cheers]
[TSUMUGI]
Natsume,
this performance
really is like magic!
You complained that
magic doesn't work on me,
and I know it was a joke.
But still, it isn't true.
Your magic's been working
on me this whole time!
After I burn this to
ashes once and for all,
my work will be done.
A nobody like me helped
start a revolution,
and if that's not good enough,
I don't know what is.
I'm proud of myself.
Thank you for that, Eichi.
[NATSUME] I see. So you
really are a good person.
[gasps]
[TSUMUGI]
Little Namie--I mean, Natsume.
How long have you been there?
Long enough.
So long as your burning things,
could you throw this on, too?
I don't mind, but what is it?
[NATSUME] A pipe dream
that never came true, sadly.
I held onto it because
I couldn't give it up.
But now that I think of it, that
was just an escape from reality.
So hurry up and burn it.
'Kay, sure.
Uh!
Hey. You ever want
things to go back?
[TSUMUGI]
Huh?
'Cause if you do, then you
probably shouldn't burn it.
Maybe someone else'll
find it someday--
someone who could actually
make that dream come true.
No, it's not like that.
I never want to go back.
I see.
I plan to move forward.
Dwelling in the past doesn't
help to improve the present.
Eichi ended it with the least
possible amount of sacrifice.
[TSUMUGI] Still... we had
to forfeit many things.
So from here on out,
I wanna do all that I can
to recover those things.
And I wanna make amends
to all the people we hurt
to compensate them somehow.
Where do you plan
to go from here?
The Five Eccentrics
have been dispersed,
leaving you with nothing
but your own talent.
You talk like you're
discussing the weather,
but a lot of this
was your doing, right?
Eichi and I did
have a hand in it.
And that's part of why
I'm so worried about you.
Look, I'm fully aware
that I have no right
whatsoever to ask this of you,
but, if you're interested
and available,
I would be incredibly honored
if you would help me out.
You have the gall to say
that to someone you crushed?
You really are the worst,
man, you know that?
[TSUMUGI] If you're still
angry with me, punch me again.
I mean, that's better
than walking away
without saying anything.
Don't you think?
[NATSUME] I'm never
gonna thank you for this.
Can't stand the thought.
But it's not like I have
anything better to do.
So, okay.
What? You mean it?
If I'm around you all the time,
then the guilt will torment
you even more, right?
That's gonna be
my sweet revenge.
When you try to sleep at night,
I'll whisper all your
worst fears to you.
Well, then I'm gonna get
the best sleep of my life!
Because you have an amazingly
soothing voice, Natsume!
Heh.
Even if it takes a lifetime,
you'll repay your debt.
I'll stay at your side,
until death do us part.
Wait a second.
Now it sounds like
I'm proposing to you.
[laughs]
[ANZU] At the time, I didn't
even know this had happened.
It wasn't until a little
while later that I learned
about this conversation
between Aoba and Sakasaki.
But as I sat up in the booth,
watching their concert,
even though I knew they had
almost given up at one point,
I felt an enormous
respect for them,
because they chose to
pick themselves back up
and try again.
So then, what do you think?
You want a Tanabata
Festival event. I see.
So we could keep
this up annually.
Your idea to use paper strips
instead of light sticks
is quite clever.
Wishes will be written
on the paper strips,
and the winning team makes one
of the fans' wishes come true--
a unique premise.
Though, I think the highlight
of this proposal lies elsewhere.
[NAZUNA]
Hey, guys! Listen!
So when two units compete,
the winning unit gets to stay
on stage no matter what.
But if the losing
unit feels like it,
they can get on a waitlist.
Once their name comes up, they
can re-enter the competition
and try to do better.
Uh, Big Bro?
What does all of that mean?
Basically, it means that
as long as there's time,
we can get onstage and
perform as much as we want.
Even if we lose, we can
still try to make a comeback!
[HAJIME, TOMOYA, MITSURU]
Ooh!
You guys, the Tanabata Festival!
We'll challenge AKATSUKI there.
And, the best part is,
this'll give us a chance
to keep improving!
--[HAJIME, TOMOYA] All right!
--[MITSURU] Heck, yeah!
[EICHI chuckles]
These rules have a
slight hint of defiance.
Is this proposal your
attempt at revolution?
I've never been
quite that ambitious.
I just thought, this way,
everybody could
give it their all
without worrying about
getting eliminated.
[EICHI]
Anzu.
This proposal's great.
I am approving it.
I did it!
You were right about that girl.
Yes. She's done well.
[EICHI]
Better than expected.
She might have influenced
me a little, too.
There's something I'd like to
try now after that last DreFes.
[MIKA]
Aww. Hey, Teach, wait up!
Why do you always leave
performances in such a hurry?
Don't you wanna interact with
the audience at least a little?
We know there's
nothing to be gained
from flattering the commoners.
So why pretend otherwise?
I perform well.
That's all I owe them,
and that's all they'll get.
[MIKA]
How'd I do at today's concert?
Good, huh? I felt like I really
nailed the choreography.
You had your moments,
but there's plenty
of room for improvement.
You have good instincts,
but you lack precision.
Aww. Come on, Teach, you don't
have to be so mean all the time.
[SHU gasps]
Hello, it's been
quite a while, Itsuki.
Sorry...
...Valkyrie.