[STUDENT A]
They're here! It's fine!
[STUDENT B]
That's Aoba and Tenshouin!
[STUDENT C] You guys were
amazing at the DreFes yesterday!
Thanks so much,
we appreciate it!
We're grateful for your support.
[STUDENTS screaming, chattering]
[TSUMUGI] Goodness! fine's
gotten really popular, huh?
You're part of the unit, too.
I know that, but
the main reason fine's
become this big of a deal
is because of you, Eichi.
First, you took over as
Student Council President.
Then you created the DreFes,
allowing the audience
to give points to the idols.
And you beat the Five
Eccentrics, fair and square.
[EICHI] I wanted to make
the vague concept of an idol's
strength into something like an
interactive game with points,
and somehow people
believed in it.
But you're even responsible
for the numbers.
I'm surprised
nobody's noticed yet.
[EICHI] Well, the finishing
touches still aren't quite done.
Uh...
[ANZU] This is what took
place about six months
before I enrolled as
a student at Yumenosaki Academy.
It's the untold story of how
an ambitious revolutionary
became a lonely emperor.
[ANZU] At the time,
the school was overflowing
with an almost electric energy.
The idea that anyone could have
their moment to shine as long
as they worked hard enough
filled the students' hearts
with hopes that their
dreams would come true.
However, that hope only felt
realistic after the geniuses
called the Five Eccentrics were
suddenly made into villains.
[TSUMUGI]
That's right.
If you don't come back
by tomorrow, then--
--[click]
--Hello?
Are you there?
Where'd Nagisa fly
off to this time?
He said something
about a Kitora Tomb.
Is that in another country?
And Hiyori is out living
it up with your money--
taking a bunch of fangirls
out and celebrating.
[gasps]
[TSUMUGI] Oh, wait,
the Kitora Tomb is in Nara?
That's actually not far away.
I'll go ahead and
have Hiyori come back
in exchange for
an increased stipend.
You're getting good at this.
[TSUMUGI] Why, thank you,
but I'm just doing my job
as the mediator of fine, and
I've been trained by the best.
You're still the genius
who's calling the shots.
I craft the orders from a safe
distance, and you give them.
Do you think that
makes me cruel?
No, you're just savvy and smart,
because in the unlikely event
something happens to fine,
you could just let me go
and continue with the
unit completely unscathed.
You're a strange
one, you know that?
Whether we're talking
casually, or about business,
your tone always
seems to be this light.
Because it's still me talking.
The brain produces
the same amount of chemicals
for any subject I speak about.
The thing is, you treat it
like it's not your problem.
Why do you criticize
everything I do?
I'll end up hating
you if you don't stop!
Crap, I'm so sorry. I didn't
mean it. I could never hate you!
[EICHI]
Hey, come here.
Isn't that...?
[TSUMUGI]
Oh! Yeah, that's Rei, I think.
Rei! Is that you?
Tsumugi. Hey.
[TSUMUGI]
I can't believe it!
I didn't know you
were back from England.
Looks like you've been
keeping pretty busy, yourself.
I always knew you would
make it big if you tried.
Thanks! I owe it all
to everyone in fine!
You know what's weird?
I'm so used to English
I can't read kanji anymore.
Look.
What's that say?
Wait, where?
[REI]
I caught you.
[TSUMUGI gasps]
What are you doing?
[REI] You should
really be more careful.
fine's the top unit in the
school right now, isn't it?
You can't risk getting into
trouble and being exposed
to things that could
be considered evil.
--[REI] Tickle, tickle...
--[TSUMUGI laughing]
Hey, cut it out!
[laughs]
Have so many bad things happened
that there's nothing left
inside of you to hurt?
If you can't feel pain,
it's the same as being dead.
I wouldn't say that exactly.
[EICHI]
Excuse me, sir.
[BOTH grunt]
[EICHI] The school rules
were recently amended.
That is now considered
an act of violence.
He didn't mean it that way.
Oh, is that so?
Don't you dare smile
at me like that, bastard.
So you're in a position
to make rules at will now?
You must think that makes
you some kind of god.
Aren't we bitter?
You had the power and the
qualifications to prevent this,
but you failed to act.
You've sinned
against your peers.
You swooped in
soon as I left.
That's the move of a coward.
[EICHI] People always want
the reason for their discontent
and worry to be anything
other than themselves.
I gave the source
of that unsightliness
the name of the
"Five Eccentrics."
And that is all I did.
Yeah, I don't believe that.
There were several incidents
that popped up at sister
schools around the world.
Those were your doing, right?
You're such a good guy--
always the compassionate one,
there to lend your
friends a helping hand.
And yet, for these emergencies,
ones that only you can
truly resolve, you're here.
You think there's nothing to
be done at Yumenosaki Academy?
Please.
[EICHI]
Well...
...your love for others
will be your downfall.
You'll be crushed to death by
the weight of your own empathy.
You're being cut to pieces
and poisoned to death by love,
and you don't even
realize it, Mr. Hero.
[REI]
Maybe you're right--
there isn't anything
left for me to do here,
in which case, my only option
is to leave you with your curse.
So be it.
You've already been
doing this for so long.
You're prepared.
[inaudible]
[EICHI] That's the
highest praise, truly.
I appreciate you, good sir.
[exhales]
Are you okay?
You look a little pale.
I need you to
stay back, Tsumugi.
At least for now,
until he's out of my sight.
[TSUMUGI gasps]
Eichi!
[SAGAMI] They said an employee
would come to get him.
Wasn't someone supposed
to come automatically?
They had to have seen that
Eichi's gauge was getting low.
[SAGAMI] He might have turned
off the transmission function.
I know he's supposed to perform
at DreFes with you tomorrow,
but I wouldn't recommend it.
Not sure how to prevent that.
He's obsessed over this
performance for months.
[SAGAMI] There's nothing
more we can do today.
You should go home.
Did you turn off
your gauge, Eichi?
Why would you ever gamble
with your own life like that?
What the...?
That's strange.
I wonder why the
door was left open?
[TSUMUGI]
No way.
[knocking]
[TSUMUGI]
Natsume?
Natsume? You in here?
[TSUMUGI yelps]
[NATSUME grunts]
Well, if it isn't Tsumugi.
[NATSUME] Bold of you
to show your face around here,
don't you think, Mr. fine?
[TSUMUGI] I'm sorry,
the door was left open.
I figured that meant
it was okay to come in.
It was open?
I must've gotten distracted.
I'd love to know what it is
that you've been working on!
Like I'd tell you.
You're the enemy, remember?
I was excited just thinking
about talking to you
because we haven't
in such a long time.
I saw how busy you were.
I'm sure being one of the Five
Eccentrics is a lot to handle.
[NATSUME] Please don't
say that name around me.
I might throw up.
'Kay! So why don't we ask
Eichi to change the name
if you guys don't like it?
--[NATSUME grunts]
--[TSUMUGI gasps]
What the hell?
Do you not feel anything?
[TSUMUGI]
Huh?
I'm bleeding right
in front of you.
My blood is dripping
from the blade
that you stabbed into my back.
[gasps, grunts]
Why would you say that?
I don't see any blood.
Seriously? Are you that dumb?
It's not just that
fine was the unit
to finally beat us in matches.
They're also the ones
who ruined our lives.
Wait, are you talking
about everything
that went on with Valkyrie?
Because it was all caused
by some crazy fine fan.
And that's the most repulsive
thing about you guys--
you never want to get
your own hands dirty.
I think it's kinda like magic,
and Eichi's actually
pretty good at it.
If you knew and
didn't try to stop it,
then you're basically
an accomplice!
[TSUMUGI] But I didn't
have a reason to stop it.
[NATSUME grunts]
Everyone who acted on fine's
behalf was happy to do it.
So you're making excuses now?
If we don't take a risk
and start a revolution,
then destruction's--
[NATSUME]
You think that's all it takes?
You say it's a "noble cause"
and suddenly we should be
grateful you stepped on us?
I understand, but
Eichi's trying to save
as many people
from harm as he can.
That's why if there's anyone
in the world who's trying
to keep him from this
mission, as his friend,
I'd have to step in
and protect him.
[NATSUME grunts]
You call him a friend?
Is that what you
actually believe?
Every member of fine is bound
by a contract, aren't they?
Well, yeah, but that's
just a formality.
[NATSUME]
Go home.
[EICHI]
Where am I?
I guess I must've fainted.
[sighs]
[EICHI]
Did I push myself too hard?
I feel like I'll die
if I have to relax.
I can't die yet.
I don't want to die.
I don't wanna die.
I don't want to die!
Let me get this straight.
I'm supposed to be
the villain in this story?
[gasps] Hibiki?
Hey, we're costars now,
no need to be so formal.
Let me say you've
picked the right guy,
I know how to commit to a role.
So you're the
sensitive ingénue,
I'm the evil villain--
This really is a tragic
comedy, isn't it?
You know what you have to do!
Find a knife and stab
the wicked in the heart!
Do you want something from me?
What is it?
[WATARU]
I do!
I still don't quite
understand my motivation.
It's confusing.
I'm going to need
better direction.
Right, why come to me?
Where are Nagisa and Hiyori?
They're the stars
of fine, after all.
Even, Tsumugi the mediator,
would've been more helpful.
Because even in a script
this poorly written,
I can recognize the creative
mastermind behind it.
It is you, Tenshouin Eichi.
[EICHI]
He called me by my name.
The one who has always
been so far away.
You give every indication
of understanding
the mechanics of my mind.
You knew exactly
what would happen
if you insisted that
I go last, didn't you?
[EICHI] I knew I could trust a
passionate, perfectionist actor.
And I found that in you.
I trusted you wouldn't ruin
the last act with some adlib.
You would honor the script
and die as planned,
even as the villain.
But I...
I don't...
I don't want to see you los--
[WATARU]
Shh.
Don't you dare say another word.
If you finish that sentence,
I'll scorn you for life.
You're an idol,
so lock those feelings away
in the closet of your heart.
That's not fair.
You're exactly right.
But that's just how you are,
which is the reason I...
Hibiki?
[EICHI]
I'll see him tomorrow...
...onstage, when
my vision's realized.
It feels like it's
finally happening.
[footsteps]
[NATSUME]
Master.
[WATARU]
Hmm?
Natsume! You came to support us!
What a surprise!
Such a good boy!
Oh, yes, you are!
Hey, quit petting me like that!
I'm not a dog!
Well, you seem pretty relaxed
for someone who has to battle
those fine devils today.
Being on stage
is all I care about!
[NATSUME] Is it true
what Big Brother Rei said?
Are you planning
to lose, Master?
Firstly, why do
you call me "Master,"
but call Rei "Big Brother"?
It's not like I'm teaching you
anything, so it's confusing!
Because even though
you're not trying,
I am learning a lot
by watching you.
Not sleight-of-hand party
tricks, real, practical magic!
[WATARU]
Hmm.
No.
You're observing carelessness
in the spirit world.
Someone cast an
evil spell on me.
Now please be a dear and
close that envelope, will you?
[NATSUME] You're only able to
act according to the script.
Since that's the case, then
all I had to do is prepare
an outline where the
Five Eccentrics beat fine.
I put everything
I had into writing this.
I stayed up night after night,
even begged people
I don't like for help.
So it's time to
change the story!
Don't the Five Eccentrics have
the right to a happy ending?
Of course we do,
but not in this way.
If we trample on others
for our own victory,
then the only thing
we've truly achieved
is becoming the
monsters ourselves.
Isn't that right, Rei?
[REI]
How'd you know I was here?
That doesn't matter, does it?
Shouldn't you be overseas
instead of wasting
time in this place?
There he is--
our demon king overflowing with
more human kindness than anyone.
Believe me,
I know I'm lucky to have one
such as you caring for me.
Well, if it were up to me,
I'd go with Natsume's
plan in a heartbeat.
He put a lot into it.
He even allowed
his eyes to get puffy.
[WATARU] Knowing that you
support it gives me reassurance
and allows me to be content with
any hardships that may come
my way. So, thank you, Natsume.
And thanks to you
as well, Rei...
...for all the days
I spent with you.
Memories of our youth--
they shine down now like...
...like, uh...
Oh, no.
I'm really not any good
at speaking with my own words.
Let's go see how
it all plays out.
We can watch from
the box seats.
Hey! Put me down, please!
I wasn't done
talking to him yet!
[REI]
It's no use struggling!
[NATSUME]
I said, let go!
[REI] You can't
escape the demon king!
So delightfully typical.
That's the Five Eccentrics.
My dear brethren.
I hope you know
how I loved you all.
[WATARU]
Goodbye, my friends,
and the cherished
days of my youth.
Until we meet again.
[CROWD chattering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
In this DreFes battle,
we've got Aoba
Tsumugi's unit, fine...
...up against one of the
Five Eccentrics, Hibiki Wataru,
--with his unit, Thirteenth Day!
--[CROWD booing]
How's it even possible
for everyone in the school
to hate the Five
Eccentrics this much?
Strange, isn't it, fine members?
Where's the rest
of your unit, Eichi?
We don't like to mix
business and relationships.
This has become a job.
Our friendships are unraveling.
Even so, we will perform
today, whatever the cost,
because that is what
our contract says.
Be honest--you don't have
any friends, do you?
I hope that's not judgment
I hear in your voice.
I have friends and you don't!
I'm not saying that makes
me better than you, though.
[WATARU] I know you brought
them to me by chance,
the ones you called
the Five Eccentrics.
With all my heart, I thank you.
[TSUMUGI]
Eichi!
Something's wrong
with my contract.
It says this is my
last performance,
and that I'll be dismissed
immediately after
along with Nagisa and Hiyori.
Yes, what's
confusing about that?
It's the same
contract everyone got.
I'm the only member
left after today.
[gasps]
Haven't you been ready for
this to end for some time now?
You don't want to hurt
or manipulate people,
or take part in crafting
strategies to sabotage them.
You've done enough.
It's time to move on.
Thanks for everything.
You were far more useful
than I imagined you'd be.
[TSUMUGI grunts]
I don't get what's happening.
I didn't do all this for you
'cause of some contract.
I thought it was a formality.
I didn't even read
it until just now.
You were good at being a friend.
Most people are when
there's money attached.
Am I wrong?
[WATARU] Aoba Tsumugi,
as I live and breathe,
I have never seen anyone
play the fool better!
I must say, you're
absolutely amazing!
I believed in him.
That he would bring change
and make everyone happy.
[gasps]
The truth is, nobody can
force happiness upon anyone.
It's not something people
can even give each other.
The most we can ever do is help.
We are responsible
for our own happiness.
It's up to us how
we choose to feel.
[TSUMUGI grunts]
[WATARU]
Are you ready to start?
Everything you've been
working toward since
the very beginning is
about to come to fruition!
So put on your masks!
Lock reality away in
the closet of your heart!
And let's celebrate
a rose-colored life!
[WATARU laughs]
Our mission is almost complete,
and this story is rapidly
heading toward a finale.
[TSUMUGI]
What's gonna happen...
...after it's over?
[WATARU] It's time. Are you
ready for our losing moment?
Another round as the
Mysterious Masked Hokke?
Ready.
[CROWD cheering]
[EICHI] The truth is,
I'm also wondering...
...what is going to
happen to us after this?
I was only able
to reach this point
because you always
supported me as a friend.
You believed in me and
gave without expectations.
[EICHI] Please, please,
don't make that face.
It's killing me.
So be it.
You've been doing
this for so long.
You're well prepared.
[REI] You sacrifice
valuable people who
have come into your life for the
sake of your twisted agendas,
instead of cherishing
them as friends.
[REI]
What a pity.
[EICHI]
Tsumugi...
...looking back...
...maybe we should
have placed more value
on the smaller things
that brought us happiness...
...like normal high schoolers.
[ANZU] And that is the story
of how Tenshouin took control
over every aspect of performance
at Yumenosaki Academy.
Even now, he reigns
over it as the "emperor."
[CROWD chattering]
[STUDENT 11D]
Hello?
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
Thank you for
coming to the show.
[TSUMUGI]
I'll never forget that day,
or the look on Eichi's face
when I left him on
stage all by himself.
[NATSUME]
Come on, you guys!
We're not gonna get anything
done staring at a blimp.
Let's get back to our rehearsal.
[SORA]
Woo-hoo! Yes, Master!
It's rehearsal time!
[TSUMUGI]
However...
...I know for a fact that I
won't make that mistake again.
I'm ready to create a new
story with my new friends,
Natsume and Sora.
But, that may have to wait.
It looks like we'll
be watching their story
for just a little while longer.
[HOKUTO grunts]
--[HOKUTO gasps]
--I hope you'll accept
this gift I brought.
I don't understand
what this means.
Non, non. You have
to look more carefully.
--[HOKUTO gasps]
--Behold this love letter
I composed as a testament
of my feelings for you!
Wait! You're about to miss
the brilliant joke I left!
Check the return address
to see who sent it!
Says Grandma?
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
For the match between Ra*bits
and Trickstar, we've tallied the
votes and the results are in.
The winner is...
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
...Trickstar!
[CROWD clapping, cheering]
Grandma wrote this? How strange.
[ANZU]
After their victory,
Trickstar began working
on their next performance--
the finals!