[STUDENTS murmuring]
[STUDENT 7A]
Hey, come be my producer!
--Sorry.
--[STUDENT 7B] Mine, too!
No way.
What is this?
[HOKUTO] Akehoshi, what are
these guys doing here?
Hey, where ya been? You're late!
So we beat Akatsuki at
the S1 yesterday, right?
And of course, after that,
everyone started
talking about Anzu.
[MAKOTO]
Behind every winning performance
is a great producer, right?
[SUBARU]
And now everyone's here to try
and recruit her to
produce their units!
A lot of people thought
the Student Council
was unbeatable, but maybe now
they're willing to fight.
[SOUMA]
Disperse, you scoundrels!
Heed my words now
or stain my blade!
--[STUDENT 7A] What the...?
--[STUDENT 7B] Is that--?
The appointed hour for
homeroom is upon us.
All of you return with haste
to your assigned classrooms.
This is a place of learning!
[STUDENTS yelp]
No, Kanzaki, don't brandish
weapons in the classroom!
Thank you for stepping in.
It's a surprise.
I didn't expect you
to help her out.
We will be vindicated,
but to a peer in need,
I shall always offer my aid.
What's more, you honored us
with a thrilling performance.
What?
[SOUMA]
I am grateful for the privilege
of sharing a stage
with such talent.
We face a worthy opponent.
I must redouble my efforts.
[ALL gasp]
[SOUMA]
That being said.
I also come bearing a
letter from Sir Hasumi.
From the vice president?
Is he mad at us because
of the S1 yesterday?
No. Sir Hasumi is fair
and just and guided
in all things by reason.
Farewell to you, Trickstar.
--My work is done.
--[school bell rings]
Morning.
[SAGAMI] Is Otogari late?
That's not like him.
[SOUMA] But if Sir Adonis were
to encounter someone in need,
his kind nature might
compel him to lend a hand.
[KOGA] I'm gonna do it.
Well, Adonis, any objections?
Um, shouldn't we
ask Sakuma first?
[KOGA]
There's nothing to ask!
If we back down from this,
Undead will be disgraced!
[ADONIS sighs]
[HOKUTO] The student council
president suddenly
made contact last night,
and now we're getting summoned?
What is the enemy
trying to do here?
Doesn't it kind of feel like
everybody's staring at us?
We did beat Akatsuki yesterday.
We're a big deal.
That's true, but
they're too scared
of the student council
to talk to us.
So I guess the revolution
is just getting started.
[SHINOBU]
Whoosh!
I beg your pardon,
Sir Yuuki and companions!
Hey, Shinobu. What's the matter?
Is this your lunch break?
Ah, yes, indeed, it is.
[MAKOTO] Everyone,
Sengoku is a first year
and he's on the broadcast
committee with me.
He's also part of
the ninja association.
[ANZU]
Ninja?
Though I am still but a
ninja in training, myself.
And I must confess
that, at the moment,
I am the organization's
sole member.
You helped out with
the S1, right?
Working on all the
behind-the-scenes stuff
with Nito and the others?
I am a member of the
broadcast committee.
I was simply doing my duty!
But still, your
performance last night
was incredibly moving!
Even our commander appeared
to be quite impressed
with your abilities.
Away! Nin, nin!
[SUBARU]
Isn't he supposed to disappear?
In the end,
I'm glad we decided
to put it all on the line.
We have to show
the student council
that there's a limit
to what people will take.
I say we answer their summons
and face them head-on.
We're here!
[EICHI] Welcome to the
Yumenosaki Academy
student council room.
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
I'm Tenshoin Eichi,
student council president.
[TORI] Hey, slave.
Pour me some tea, too!
It's been so long since I've
talked with the president
this much, and my
throat's getting dry!
I am nobody's slave, Tori.
[TORI grumbles]
[giggles]
It's time to pay
the price, Trickstar.
No more games!
The president has returned,
and you're all gonna go kaboom!
There's no need to be rude.
I only called them here to talk,
not to pick a fight with them.
Wow, you'd even take pity
on these rotting piles of trash.
You're so gracious!
[clears throat] There is
nothing to discuss.
We didn't come here to try
and make nice with you.
Don't waste our time.
Hold on. I like the
student council room.
Everything's so sparkly!
This is getting really tense--
can we please go back?
[HOKUTO] Akehoshi,
you're way too relaxed.
And, Yuuki, you're
way too uptight.
Can't you just act normal?
[EICHI laughs]
Great chemistry, very funny.
[EICHI]
I'll get straight to the point.
[ALL gasp]
[EICHI] The unit called
Trickstar is no more.
--[ALL gasp]
--What, because you said so?
You may be the student council,
but you don't have the
power to just shut us down!
I can't accept this.
We're not done! Trickstar
is only getting started!
Shut up. Ya insects!
No way. Stop this!
You have no right!
Calm down.
Don't take that tone
with upperclassmen.
That aside. I have my own
issues with this idea, Eichi.
Since their win
at yesterday's S1,
Trickstar's popularity
has skyrocketed.
There are a lot of
people who believe
that they're the heroes
this school needs.
If we force them to break up,
then we're the villains.
That's so kind of you
to stand up for the kids
who humiliated you in
public only yesterday.
I'm simply thinking of what's in
the student council's interest.
[EICHI] I would not be making
this move unless I knew
it would work out
to the mutual benefit
of everyone involved.
I assure you.
If all of you just
follow the script,
the story will end happily.
[gasps]
What are you doing!
Put me down right now, slave!
I'm sorry, Tori.
But we'll have plenty of time
to play later, up on stage.
[gasps] Yeah! Bye, President!
[HOKUTO]
"On stage"?
Now, then. Though
it is sad to say,
I must insist that you disband.
But of course, I won't allow
such talent to go to waste.
You'll all be great assets
to our more prominent units.
[GROUP gasps]
[EICHI]
Indeed.
Hidaka Hokuto and
Akayhoshi Subaru.
I invite you both to
join my group, fine.
[TRICKSTAR gasps]
This is the academy's top unit,
and I want you two with us.
[gasps]
For all our sakes, this
school, this whole industry,
I want your talents to grow.
And of course, I would not
forget your fellow members.
Isara Mao.
Keito holds you in high regard
and would have
you join Akatsuki.
And Yuuki Makoto,
you've caught the eye
of one of our
most popular units.
Knights tell me they
want you for their own.
Huh?
[EICHI] Aside from
council-affiliated groups,
they're the strongest
in the school,
veterans with a long tradition.
This is an opportunity
that students
of your caliber rarely see,
Yuuki. Don't let it pass.
[MAKOTO grunts]
Of course, the student
council cannot force you.
You can fight us,
but you won't win.
Although you may have fun
with it for a little while.
Your revolution will
go up in flames.
How could you?
[EICHI] I'm just looking
out for the students
of Yumenosaki Academy.
Of course, you will be rewarded.
I know I'm asking
a great deal of you.
[ALL gasp]
[EICHI] So let's start with
10,000,000. How's that sound?
[HOKUTO]
You're trying to buy us off?
[EICHI]
Akayhoshi Subaru.
I believe you're quite fond
of money, aren't you?
You shut your mouth.
I don't want any
of your dirty money,
'cause that stuff
doesn't sparkle at all!
So you won't accept paper?
I didn't bring any gold or gems.
You're a true original,
as expected.
It must run in the family.
I'll have to take
a different approach.
Yuuki Makoto.
[gasps]
[EICHI] The unit that will
exhibit your natural talent
to the fullest is not
Trickstar. It's Knights.
You'll be working with
Narukami and Sena,
two of the best models
in the entire industry.
They will help you shine.
I'm an idol, not a model. You--
And is Trickstar making use
of your talent as an idol?
It felt to me like
you were only there
to make them look better.
[HOKUTO]
Don't listen to him!
[EICHI]
Hidaka Hokuto.
I have already made
arrangements with your family.
In fact, they bowed
to me in gratitude
and asked me to take
good care of you.
My parents have nothing
to do with this!
[EICHI]
You need to grow up.
[gasps]
[EICHI] I've been blessed
with many things,
but time is not one of them.
I wish to make the best
of everything I was given.
You think I don't?
[EICHI]
Your father is an acclaimed idol
with an ongoing career,
and your mother is a
top actress in her prime.
Are you really content
to squander such privilege?
[HOKUTO gasps]
And Isara Mao.
You've managed to
balance school, idol work,
and student council activities.
I know you're sharp
enough to understand
what's being offered.
Please excuse me.
It's about time for my concert.
It's a B1, so you won't
need a ticket to watch.
Isara, would you
escort them, please?
[MAO]
Yes, sir.
Observe closely, everyone,
and imagine what you
could become a part of.
There will also be a small
announcement after the show.
That's all. I'll be
awaiting your responses.
[MAKOTO] I don't think
a student council unit
has ever competed in
a B1 before, have they?
That's right.
Well, normally,
Akatsuki just looks the
other way during the B1s.
They don't think it's
even worth their time.
They only step in when
things get out of hand,
like at the Ryuu-ou-sen
the other day.
Except now, things
are so different.
Tenshouin Eichi has come back,
and this paradise of ours
is in his sights.
To him, it's just
territory to conquer.
He truly is like an emperor.
[electric guitar strums]
[music plays]
Adonis, what are you doing!
Quit staring at
the thing and play!
I'm sorry, but it feels
so small and delicate.
I worry I'll break it.
[SUBARU]
Gami- san . Occhan.
Does this mean that fine's
going to be competing
with Undead?
[REI] Our overeager puppy
pounced at their challenge.
Once he got the
letter, he accepted
without giving it
a second thought.
Undead got involved
in the S1 yesterday
to help make you all look good.
I'm afraid that,
after our little stunt,
the mongrel is feeling
a bit restless.
[KOGA grunts]
[REI] And I've never been
much good with sunlight.
An outdoor concert in
the middle of the day
would be a disaster for me.
Where's Hakaze Kaoru?
[REI] He's mad at me for
tricking him into performing
last night, so he just took
off for who-knows-where.
Meaning that the unit's
two biggest draws
are missing from the show.
Undead's real strength
has been sealed off.
It is truly frightening.
Tenshouin has the
face of an angel,
but in his heart lies
the cruelty of a demon.
[KEITO] Are you using this B1
to make an example out of them?
I'm not as kind a person as you.
I can't afford to be.
I don't know how long
I have before I'm forced
to return to the hospital.
There's no time to relax.
The whole entertainment
sector in this country,
including idols, is
becoming industrialized.
There are still outliers.
Some individuals can still
stand apart from the crowd.
But even the most
talented performer
can never compete with a factory
working at peak productivity.
Hard work and natural
ability can make a hero,
but consistency and efficiency
can build entire armies.
[KEITO] Is that what
you're after, an army?
Not for myself exactly.
I mean to raise an army
for the idol industry.
I want to create a
legion of happy slaves,
who love nothing
more than to serve.
I will lead this country's
idols and lift them up
to the height of culture.
[WATARU] Hokuto, you're making
such a serious face!
Won't you smile for me now?
The universe can be
such a cold, dark place,
but a smile always shines like
a shooting star in the night!
A smile is hope, desire,
love! Right, Hokuto?
It's the Masked Pervert.
I'll shine my love
into the universe today.
For I am your beloved
Hibiki Wataru!
You know him?
Yes, but I try not
to acknowledge it
unless I absolutely have to.
Unfortunately,
he's the president
of the theatre club I'm in.
[WATARU grunts, laughs]
Amazing!
[CROWD cheers]
Ugh, why did the president
bring in the creepy guy
with the long hair?
It's been said many
times that Master Hibiki
possesses extraordinary talent.
And with his
inimitable personality,
he's earned his place among
the Three Eccentrics.
In terms of raw ability,
he may even be a match
for the president himself.
[TORI]
You take that back!
[EICHI]
It's been too long.
Tori, Yuzuru, and you, Wataru.
Finally the awaited
hour has come.
Our Eichi makes his triumphant
return to the stage!
Now then, without delay.
Let's Begin!
[CROWD cheers]
[HOKUTO]
They're incredible.
It's like I can hear
a whole orchestra
on stage with them, playing
a beautiful symphony.
His name was Fushimi, right?
He's a great talent.
A natural support player
who can bring
the other members' strong
personalities together
to form a top-class unit.
Himemiya. Even though
he messes up a lot,
you can barely see
the mistakes through
the shine of his character.
But most impressive of all
is the student council
president, Tenshouin Eichi!
Every note and step
is beyond perfection.
And he just got out
of the hospital?
He's truly a top idol!
Maybe it's actually
for the best.
I'm proud of what
we've done. I am.
But would it really be so wrong
if we accepted the
president's offer?
Isara, you can't--
[MAO]
It would be a huge step up.
We would all be reaching
new heights in our careers.
And with the student
council's backing,
we can still make a difference,
even if Trickstar goes away,
we could work from the inside
and change the system
for the better.
Wait. Are you serious?
Isara, please.
Yeah, I mean it.
I'm not saying this as
a student council member.
Just think about it.
[CROWD cheers]
[EICHI]
Thank you.
I'd like to make a brief
announcement to all of you
as your student council
president, so please listen.
As I'm sure you all know,
there is an important event
in the idol industry
that takes place
at the end of every year.
Of course, I'm
speaking of the SS.
Idols from all
across the country,
professional and amateur alike,
compete to
distinguish themselves
as the best in the nation.
This is the ultimate
DreFes. The SS.
Anybody attending this school...
Anyone who chooses
to be an idol...
...would wish for the
opportunity to compete
on this stage and win.
And so I hereby proclaim!
Every unit in Yumenosaki
Academy is invited
to compete for the
right to represent us
at the SS in a DreFes!
We call this
competition the DDD.
A competition to determine
which unit should
carry our school's banner on
the industry's biggest stage.
This is a chance for all
of you to put your abilities
as idols on full display
and shine your brightest.
I hope to see everyone
participate in the DDD.
And needless to say,
we of fine will also
be taking part.
So reach for your desires,
harness your passion,
and face this challenge.
I want to hear your
voices resound!
Ensembles, give us your all!
[SUBARU] I can't believe
it's only two more weeks
until the DDD!
That's not much time
for something so big.
We'll have a lot of
special training again,
but I know we can take on fine,
just like we did with Akatsuki.
We're Trickstar!
Nothing can stop us!
I'm sorry.
Hokke? Where you going?
Hey, hold on!
You can hear me, right?
I know you can, I'm right here.
Hokke! Why are you ignoring me?
Friends don't do that!
Don't just walk away from me!
Hokuto!
[HOKUTO] I never expected
to hear you call me
by my real name
at a time like this.
[gasps]
[HOKUTO] I'm going to go
talk to the president
about his offer.
About my future.
And Isara and Yuuki.
I'm sure they'll do the same.
[gasps]
[HOKUTO]
It really was fun. Thank you.
Working with you
was the first time
I actually liked being an idol.
Huh?
You showed me the
light of hope,
and I pray that you'll
keep it shining bright.
[SUBARU]
What was that?
It sounded like a real goodbye.
You shouldn't joke
around like that.
I'm not laughing.
This isn't funny!
Hokuto. Makoto. Mao.
If I can't have all
of you beside me,
what am I supposed to do?