[music plays]
[MAKOTO exhales]
I'd say it's coming together.
What do you think?
[HOKUTO] Not bad, but there's
always room for improvement.
I think the chorus choreography
could use a little work.
Yeah, I agree,
it does need something.
Back when we first started, we
all would've been fine with it,
but that was before
we saw Adam perform. Man.
That's right! So let's
keep on aiming higher!
Then we'll crush them
all in the Autumn S1!
After that, we'll dominate
Adam in the next SS!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ANZU] The Autumn S1
Halloween Party was coming up.
After the Tanabata Festival,
I guess they decided
I was the right person to
put in charge of planning it.
And almost done!
[LEO]
Hey, Ritsu! Big day today, huh?
That why you're
taking a nap right now?
[LEO]
Hey, Ritsu!
If you're ignoring me,
this is the saddest day ever!
Wait, are you asleep?
Does this mean I'm too late?
Please don't die! We need you!
Ritsu! Ritsu!
Hey, King.
I didn't see you there.
I heard you though.
You're so loud.
Good thing I am! That was
more than just sleeping.
It looked like you passed out!
Sorry for any inconvenience.
So you were
worried about me, huh?
I'm worried that you're gonna
suddenly disappear one day!
Worry is the bane of creativity.
So that's the way it is?
You only care how
I might fit into your art.
King!
You're such a spoiled
baby, you know that?
There, there, it's fine.
Thank you. I'm really thirsty.
Can you go down
and get me a drink?
[LEO] That is not part
of my job as a unit leader.
But fine, I guess I will.
You're the best!
Welp.
[RITSU sighs]
[ANZU]
What's wrong?
Uh?
Why don't you go rest
in the infirmary?
I'm fine. It's just that
being around so many people
is like sitting out
in the sun for hours.
[gasps]
[REI] I appreciate
you telling me like this.
An enemy close by is better
than an estranged friend.
I'll move on this right away.
Thank you, Tsukinaga.
If you're close enough
to hear this announcement,
I need your attention!
The long-awaited Halloween
Party is about to begin!
This DreFes is being held by
the idols at Yumenosaki Academy!
Where else can you
see your favorite idols
dressed in costume and welcoming
you with a song and dance?
All visitors are encouraged
to wear a costume and
celebrate the event with us!
Remember this phrase,
'cause you'll need it!
[BOTH]
Knock, knock, trick or treat!
[STUDENT A]
Oh my gosh! So cute!
[NAZUNA] That's right!
We're not ordinary rabbits.
Yeah, we're creepy zombie
rabbits! Look out, we're scary!
[CHIAKI whimpers]
I just saw a real live ghost!
I believe what you saw was
a visitor in a ghost costume.
[CHIAKI yelps]
I feel something cold crawling
up and down my spine! [whimpers]
It's humid, that's all. I had no
idea Morisawa was so terrified
of paranormal folklore.
[CHIAKI yells]
Would you like a
program of the event?
[MADARA]
Hey there, Anzu!
Uh?
MaM has arrived!
'Kay?
Hey, you look amazing!
Little Red Riding Hood was
the perfect choice for you!
No special powers, but she
won't be eaten by monsters!
Um, thank you, I think.
Mikejima, right?
Sorry, I don't
recognize your costume.
I am a guardian of the
historical Valley of Kings!
However, they're more commonly
referred to as mummies.
I guess you can go ahead and
call me mummy for short.
Guess you always want
to be called something
that sounds like mama.
I've been meaning to ask
you about what you said.
You mentioned that we met before
when we were both
in kindergarten, right?
But... I don't
remember that at all.
Oh, looks like the wolf is
coming after you, Little Red.
[ANZU]
Huh?
Ogami?
Looks like he's waiting for me
to leave so he can talk to you.
I guess I'm done, then.
--Oh, no, don't do that.
--Here.
I'll finish passing out programs
for you so you can go chat.
That's okay.
Go on. Aren't you glad
we're old friends?
[KOGA] Anyway, sorry
to take up your time.
So you're a werewolf?
Clever choice, Ogami.
Yeah and you're
Little Red Riding Hood.
Roar!
Okay, fine, forget it.
You're not being fun.
That vampire bastard asked
me to do something for him.
Do ya think you could
help me out with it?
And by vampire,
do you mean Sakuma?
That's right.
Have you ever met his
little brother, Ritsu?
I call him Richie.
Anyway, this mission
I'm on has to do with him.
Apparently things
are getting worse.
What do you mean?
Recently, he's been reported to
stay wide awake during the day.
Ever since I've known him,
daytime's been
his chosen bedtime.
Oh, wow.
Vampires aren't supposed
to be awake during the day.
Not that I think they're
actually vampires,
let's be real.
But the fact remains that
both of those brothers
get weak in sunlight.
Interesting.
You know, you're a lot nicer
than you pretend to be, Ogami.
[KOGA gasps]
Things are going
well at the academy.
That's because of Trickstar.
They managed to beat the student
council president at the DDD.
But it's not entirely
because of them.
As much as I hate to say it,
that vampire
bastard helped, too.
He fought so that his dear
friends could enjoy their youth.
So what was the
point of that work
if his own brother collapses?
Why did he bother going
through all of that trouble.
You know what I mean?
Anyway, I respect that, which is
why I want to help Richie rest.
He's supposed to perform
in tonight's concert.
I want him to save
up his energy.
The infirmary is being used
as the first-aid office
for visitors, so he wouldn't
be able to rest there.
[KOGA] It's not necessary
to find a location.
The vampire bastard
already prepared a bed
for Richie in the music room.
Here's the thing.
I don't get along with Richie,
so he won't listen to me,
but I have a feeling he might
not object if it came from you.
[RITSU] What is it
you want from me, Corgi?
Why did you drag Anzu here?
[KOGA]
Who you callin' a corgi?
Your timing is perfect.
The people in charge of food
asked me to make way
too many desserts.
Look.
They told me I could keep half
of the profit after the event.
That's called easy money.
You're supposed to be conserving
your energy, remember?
Not wasting it on cupcakes!
[RITSU] Thing is, people didn't
like these ones very much,
so I tried a new recipe.
You have a performance later.
Go get some rest.
Hey, why don't you taste
test the ones I brought?
If I know someone's tried it,
I'll be able to rest.
What if Anzu tries it?
Ugh. You can't serve these.
They don't look safe
for humans to eat.
How very rude and uncultured.
These are quality desserts.
Here.
Say, "ahh."
Ahh...
[groans] No, stop!
Get away it from me!
[KOGA screams]
[RITSU] Corgi looked
so funny, didn't he?
It was so nice of him to help
me transport the desserts.
[KOGA panting]
You know, Sakuma, apart
from the appearance,
your desserts were pretty
yummy! You did a great job!
It's unfortunate that Ogami
didn't like them so much.
Nah, it's fine. I know the
Corgi doesn't like sweets.
And by the way,
I don't like being called
by my last name ever.
Please call me Ritsu.
Okay. Sorry, Ritsu.
I think that's it over there.
[RITSU]
The music room?
Now where is it? I'm not seeing
a bed anywhere around here.
Whenever I'm here, my favorite
thing to do is play piano.
[ANZU]
You can play?
[piano plays]
[RITSU]
In the beginning,
Mr. Kunugi would get mad
at me for playing so much.
Now he lets me stay
here as long as I want to.
Sometimes he even
gives me lessons.
But then Nacchan found out
and got pretty upset with me.
Who's that?
[RITSU] Narukami Arashi.
He's also in Knights.
When I first met him, I always
used to call him Nakkun,
but now he prefers
to be called Nacchan.
I don't get what
difference it makes.
I used to let little things
like that annoy me a lot.
But, then recently, I'm
finding that I'm okay with it.
I'll tolerate a lot
to not have to be alone.
It's strange.
I never thought I'd be one
of the ones who felt this way.
But still, I need to make
sure I have boundaries.
I don't want to be like brother
and lose everything
important to me.
I really am low on energy.
By the way, what is that?
[ANZU]
Oh!
That's it!
[RITSU]
Hm?
It's a special bed
just for you!
--[ANZU gasps]
--[RITSU] Hmm.
[RITSU[ It does kinda look
like a bed, doesn't it?
[ANZU]
Yeah.
[RITSU]
But if I sleep here,
I'll be like brother,
and that's not what I want.
[ANZU gasps]
I'm sorry!
I was told you also
lived like a vampire,
so that's why
I designed it like this.
[RITSU]
You designed it?
I did.
[RITSU]
Something about your reaction
earlier tells me otherwise.
Yeah, well...
It doesn't matter.
The fact remains that
I'm still quite tired.
I'll sleep here and
let you know what I think.
Yay! It's so soft.
Fascinating. I wonder why he
doesn't like his older brother.
[SORA] Woo-hoo!
He doesn't actually hate him.
[gasps]
You're being rude.
That's information you
should keep to yourself, Sora.
Pardon us, we
couldn't help overhearing.
But I could tell
it was about Rei.
So, of course, I was curious.
Look at that.
It's a little morbid,
but clearly a lot of
love went into making it.
What a complicated
and beautiful color.
[ANZU]
Huh?
Sora's good at
reading that stuff.
He's very talented
at a lot of things.
[KOGA] So what was
the point of that work
if his own brother collapses?
Why did he bother going
through all of that trouble.
You know what I mean?
[ANZU] If only he knew how
his big brother really feels.
[NAZUNA]
The special stage is now open.
Ticket holders, please be
sure to enter slightly early.
The performance will
start at six PM sharp.
[MAO]
Hey, Ritsu. Ritsu!
Uh...
The concert's going
to start soon.
Is that Maakun?
Anzu asked me to come
in here and wake you up.
Did she now?
That silly girl.
Huh?
She lies and she's
not very good at it.
Okay?
It could just be me.
There is a lot of light around.
If so, I'm very grateful to you.
You and everybody in Knights.
Thank you for the
warm rays of light
that you shone
right into my soul,
little by little, and
lighting the darkness inside.
Ritsu.
It shone in me, burned in me,
until I was almost ash.
But amazingly,
I didn't mind it at all.
I wouldn't want you to turn to
ash even if you begged for it.
[RITSU chuckles]
I wonder if my brother
ever experienced a feeling
like this way back then.
Oh, like last year?
When the student
council president's unit
defeated the Five Eccentrics?
During those earlier times,
brother was quite fond of
anything that was
bright and warm.
He tried so hard
to protect them,
even though he
knew it was impossible.
In the end, he lost everything,
including what he already had.
[RITSU]
I'm done sleep talking.
The sun has set, so I better
go get ready for the concert.
Right behind you.
And we can talk any
time you want. I mean it.
I'll get the desserts ready.
This will be so fun!
[door opens]
[HINATA]
Mr. Sakuma!
[BOTH] The concert's about to
start. Time to get ready!
[HINATA]
Huh?
Anzu?
Hi, Yuta! Hi, Hinata!
[HINATA]
What are you making?
Is it a Halloween costume?
Yeah, I'm taking in one of his
spares just in case he needs it.
Anyway, I should head
to the concert site.
[flute plays]
What's the flute for?
It's one of the best
ways to wake up Sakuma.
It's usually not long
after we play it.
Makes me feel like
a snake charmer.
[ANZU]
Oh, I see.
[ANZU gasps]
Good morning.
Is it time for breakfast yet?
[ANZU yelps]
Oh, my, what have we here?
She looks tasty.
[ANZU screams]
Cut it out!
It's no time for pranks!
She's a person, not a snack!
Ah...
What was I thinking?
I suppose you're right.
[ANZU sighs]
It's been a long time since
I've been able to feel
the warmth of a human.
It's absolutely invigorating!
Allow me to carry you to
the concert site as an apology.
[ANZU yells]
M'lady,
I see you've been successful
in making Ritsu sleep.
[ANZU]
It's nothing!
As his brother, I thank you.
I'm grateful for your time
and dedication to this.
[ANZU]
I just--
You are a rare one.
Perhaps I should lock you
away in my treasure room.
Come along, my beloved children.
The pandemonium's
about to begin.
We don't want to miss a minute!
[HINATA, YUTA]
Okay!
[KAORU]
All right, what's going on?
Isn't that supposed to
be the role I'm playing?
[REI]
It's just the way it turned out.
What happened with
the old vampire?
Did he do anything weird to you?
No, not really.
I wonder if the thing that
happened earlier
counts as weird?
That was a pretty
scandalous situation.
Interesting costume.
Are you dressed
as a priest, Kaoru?
They are enemies
of vampires, you know.
[KAORU] Yes, but it's
not what you think.
I'm the bad priest
that gobbles up girls.
I'm an ally of monsters!
If you don't believe
in God, it's okay.
You can still believe in me.
[ANZU chuckles]
[HINATA]
Wow, Otogari, nice work!
You got so much candy!
[ADONIS]
The kids gave these to me.
Usually when I go into town,
they all run away in fear,
but they seem to like
me in this costume.
Hakaze was so gracious
to help me out with it.
Thank you, sir.
Don't be silly,
all I did was encourage them.
--[DOGS barking]
--[ALL] Huh?
[KOGA laughing]
Did you just cut?
You have to wait your turn!
I'll get to all
of you, I promise.
Wow, that's a lot of dogs.
There're so many, I can hardly
tell which one is our puppy.
I'm sure you can
if you try a little harder.
Those puppies are
having so much fun!
It's funny. He's an idol, too.
Though, at the moment, it seems
like only dogs are interested.
Let's go, Puppy.
Time to hit that stage.
[KOGA]
Huh?
You think you can just
show up and make me leave?
Vampire bastard!
[DOGS whine]
Wha...? Look, I'm not mad
at you guys or anything.
Hey, pretty boy.
Hey, 2wink and UNDEAD!
We need you on standby please!
[HINATA, YUTA]
'Kay!
We figured we
should go on first.
Bats are like
our familiar spirits.
Although, that doesn't
mean we're the opening act.
Be sure to stay on
guard if you don't want us
to rip the carpet
out from under you.
I see. So you're
planning to destroy us.
Very well, then.
I wish you luck.
After all, it's Halloween, a
rare celebration where monsters
and humans intermingle,
granting each other grace.
Let's get this rampage started!
[CROWD cheers]
'Scuse me?
Hey there, what's up?
[ANZU]
Is Ritsu here?
No, he just finished performing,
so he's most likely
changing in the back room.
I have a favor to ask you.
[GROUP]
Uh?
[RITSU]
Hey, what's the deal here?
Why did you force
me to put this on?
We already finished
performing, didn't we?
Maybe so, but that doesn't
mean you're done quite yet!
It's all right to jump in during
today's concert if you
want to spice things up!
What?
[LEO]
Don't even think about it.
Go get it over with!
--[gasps]
--[CROWD cheers]
Ritsu, glad you came.
It's you.
[REI] Try to control
yourself out here.
Don't be rude to the audience.
Seriously? You're so arrogant.
Hey! What's this all about?
So did you enjoy your new bed?
Rei did it. He wanted to
make sure you got some rest.
Maybe you should thank him?
Just a suggestion.
[RITSU]
What?
[REI] It seemed like the young
lady was very considerate.
[REI]
I'm extremely grateful for her.
You're still a traitor who
always breaks his promises.
You don't get to start
playing older brother now.
You're absolutely
right. I agree.
I have no right to call
you my family anymore.
Not after the way
I left you behind.
But if I can't be your family,
at least acknowledge me
as a fellow idol student
of Yumenosaki Academy.
Even if just
for a fleeting moment,
sharing this shining
stage with all of you.
Watch closely. You'll see.
Tonight is a night
where monsters
and humans come together
to enjoy themselves.
[REI]
Sharing light and warmth.
[gasps]
[REI] Please permit me
to sing by your side
on such a blissful
night as this one.
Go ahead and sing if that's
what will make you happy.
[gasps]
[REI] Will you please let me
say one last thing before I go?
[REI] Even if you feel
you genuinely despise me,
no matter the reason,
please, always remember
to take care of yourself--
even if I am expelled
from your life.
You are precious to so
many others besides just me.
And then... when you feel
like you can't go on,
come back to me and
let me take care of you.
Thank you very much.
It's nice to know
you're the kind of person
I can always turn to.
[RITSU]
Well... okay.
I'm in a good mood today,
so I guess I'll just say it.
I apologize for
making you worry.
Thank you...
...big brother.
[REI, RITSU]
Trick or treat!