[ANZU]
The next morning,
everyone was still
talking about the S1.
"Change the future," huh?
That line inspires me no matter
how many times I hear it.
Yeah, me, too.
Aw, why'd you have
to mention it?
Don't cry, Hajime!
Bread always cheers
me up, want some?
Huh?
♪ Bread, glorious bread! ♪
Smells good. I haven't
had breakfast yet.
Take one!
I've got a round bread,
some of these swirly ones,
this one's super soft.
Oh and look: red bread!
Not to cut your
bread-fest short,
but we need to rehearse soon.
I wanna be sure Rab*its
doesn't lose again.
[BOTH]
All right!
You got it, Big Bro!
Huh? Hey, good
morning, Shinonon!
Good morning, other
Ra*bits! Hi, Nito!
You were great yesterday!
Thanks for your help at the S1!
Oh, you don't have to thank me.
Tell ya what. You can consider
it pay back for our S2.
[SUBARU giggles]
[HAJIME]
Congrats! Amazing performance!
It was the best
thing I've ever seen!
Huh? You never
stopped eating, dude.
[MITSURU] That's what I do
when I'm really moved.
And when I'm hungry.
Want some bread?
Enough, Mitsuru!
Quit being so random in
front of upperclassmen.
[SUBARU]
That smells delish!
Thank you! Uh. Hold on.
There was something I wanted
to ask you guys about.
[NAZUNA]
Mm?
Tenshouin Eichi?
But he was in the
hospital? Are you sure?
He talked to us
all after the S1.
It was a pretty big
surprise for us, too.
Oh, wow!
He's student council president
and the leader of fine.
They're the school's top idols.
He rules the school
in every way,
that's why they
call him "Emperor."
"Adventurer"? Me, too!
I like to adventure to
places where I can run!
Oh! I'd run around
the schoo--!
Hey. Can you stand still?
Not forever, just like a second.
He's the ruler of the school?
Hokke said that,
too, but I dunno.
He didn't seem all that scary
when he talked to
us all last night.
Kinda makes me wonder
what he's really like.
[NAZUNA]
What are you up to, Tenshouin?
I hope this isn't
what it looks like.
Please don't do that to them.
Bad enough you did it
to us a year ago.
[CROWD chattering]
Are you ready?
Then let us begin,
my sweet marionette.
Come on, Big Bro! Hurry up!
[NAZUNA]
Last year, around this time,
before I was in Ra*bits,
I belonged to a different unit.
That entire year,
I was a puppet
with no will of my own.
[applause]
[SAGAMI] All right,
Let's see. Open up wide.
[SAGAMI]
Hm...
I'm not seeing anything
out of the ordinary.
Not on this end.
Didn't notice many
signs of strain either.
Here's what's weird.
This usually only
happens to kids
much younger than you.
But voices change little by
little throughout our lives.
So, I'm not too
worried about it.
[STUDENT 05A]
What class? Just skip, dude.
[STUDENT 05B laughs]
Screw your grades.
All that matters
is that we go here.
[STUDENT 05C]
I know, right?
[STUDENTS laugh]
[NAZUNA] If you had to
describe Yumenosaki Academy
to somebody in one word,
it would be "corrupt."
Students rely on the school's
brand and reputation
and feel like they don't
have to put in any effort.
Because they've been shown
that that's how it works.
Some might be a little bitter.
Nito's late, yet again.
Doesn't he realize the
concert's about to start?
[MIKA]
These costumes, though!
I'm obsessed!
They're incredible!
The elaborate details
on here are stunning.
It sorta reminds me of
antique doll clothes.
What's with the tendency
to claim something's
high quality just
because it's new?
People should just be
honest and accept the truth.
Shouldn't they? "Itsuki
Shu's the best tailor!"
[MIKA] I love how Big Sis Maddy
has a matching outfit. So cute!
[SHU]
Hmph.
[MIKA]
Uh--
Yes. It does look
fabulous on Mademoiselle.
But it looks pretty
good on you, too.
For real?
Your praise means
so much to me, Teach!
[door creaks]
[panting]
Hey, Big Bro Nazuna!
Where ya been?
[MIKA] Come on, man, why are
you bowing to me like that?
You know I'm younger
than you, don't ya?
Hurry up and put
on your costume.
I'm just kidding.
[SHU] There's no way you
could put it on yourself,
so I'll have to help you!
My little marionette. Nito!
My sweet, beautiful,
adorable puppet!
[MIKA]
Take a breath, Teach.
It kinda sounds like you're
infatuated with Big Bro.
I am, Mika, I am!
So much so that it
pains me to think
of showing his brilliant,
dazzling form to the masses!
If I could, I'd keep
him all to myself.
That's why...
...we have to make it our
goal to crush the insects
squirming in between
our fingers.
And in order to do that,
we need you, my dear.
[SHU]
fine, was it?
The son from the
noble Tenshouin family
is one of their
members, so I've been
a bit curious about them.
But it seems like they're
a rich boy's hobby.
"It's whatever. They're
no match for us."
Neither is that strange group
called the Five Eccentrics
that I'm randomly a part of.
They're currently watching
and waiting to see
what we do next.
Know what I'd like
to do with fine
and the other philistines?
Pulverize them.
Then dispose of them by
stuffing them into cheap dolls.
Dispose of all the
weak and foolish!
We only want the beautiful
who are worthy
of a place in Heaven
here with us!
Yeah! Right, Teach!
[SHU laughs]
[applause]
[SHU]
Welcome!
We hope you enjoy
this delightful evening
of puppet theatre!
[NAZUNA]
That was strange.
There's usually more
of an introduction
before the performance starts.
It's like he's saying,
"keep up or you'll
be left behind."
[NAZUNA] The performance is
a beautiful miniature garden.
Everything is planned perfectly
down to the last second.
We are...
...Valkyrie.
This show invites the audience
to bask in Teach's world.
No flirting with or
flattering the audience.
Raw performance,
without compromise.
[SHU] Focus, Nito.
You're not concentrating.
You're always point-four
seconds behind everyone else.
This is a prerecorded song.
All you have to do is dance.
This isn't like you at all.
What's going on tonight?
[NAZUNA gasps]
[SHU] I am the creator of all
things, a god holding the end
of every puppet string
in this world.
I wonder...
Why is it that people
do not realize that dolls
are far superior to humans?
[NAZUNA] Ever since my
voice started changing,
I haven't been able to sing in
the range that Teach expects.
So he stopped
considering me a singer.
He has me lip-sync
through every concert.
I've been forbidden
from signing on stage.
And now, I'm nothing
more than a marionette.
Teach pulls the
strings and I dance.
[KEITO]
Itsuki Shu, second year.
He's an absolute leader.
He conceptualizes and
reviews everything himself
from the unit's
songs and costumes
to their choreography
and set design.
Nito Nazuna, second year.
He was discovered in a choir.
A soprano with a voice
like an angel's.
He's the main
attraction of the unit.
Kagehira Mika, first year.
He draws people in with
his mismatched eyes.
Other than that, he has
no special skills.
This is Valkyrie.
They are currently the unit
reigning at the top
of the school.
Although, They may be faltering.
[MIKA] I thought we killed it
during that show, didn't you?
I turned on the hot
water for the bath.
After today, we all need one--
I'm going up to
fix our costumes.
Everyone stay out.
[footsteps]
[ARASHI]
Mika! Hey!
You scared the crap
outta me, Naruchan!
I think my heart may have
stopped for a second.
You look okay to me!
Oh, ew! I take it back!
Looks like you're bleeding!
[MIKA] Am I? Wonder
how that happened.
It's my fault! I'm sorry!
It's fine, I'll just
suck on it a little.
That won't work!
You need a doctor!
[SAGAMI]
There. How do you feel?
Better. Thank you so much!
We couldn't have done this
without you! Mr. Kunugi!
Huh?
All right, please get back
to your classes now.
School isn't out just yet.
He's so indifferent and so cool!
Hey, uh. You okay there?
[ARASHI] I wanna buy you
dessert for what happened.
Get whatever you want.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Did you get invited to join
some crazy-extreme
unit recently?
I wouldn't call them extreme,
but they are really
passionate about their work.
They remind me
of the Shinsengumi,
because they'll cut
you left and right
if you mess with them
or their members!
That's considered violence
in some countries.
I don't like living by
other people's rules.
So I may actually
lay low for a while.
'Kay, but if you ever
need anything out there,
let me know.
You're beautiful.
Now. Let's get you
something delish!
I'm good! I brought
my own, actually.
[ARASHI]
Is that candy?
[MIKA] Mm-hm! Teach is always
saying it's part of his duty
to make sure I stay
healthy so I can perform
the way he wants me to.
He expects nothing less
than perfect performances.
So he makes food for me.
Which is how he ensures that
I'm always in good health!
[ARASHI]
Oh, my!
It's also why I can't grab
some dessert with you,
even though that sounds amazing.
[ARASHI]
Aw.
Also, I just remembered
that sweet Big Bro Nazuna's
birthday is coming up soon.
He's an upperclassman
who's in Valkyrie with us.
Oh, my!
[MIKA] I've been making
him a birthday present
but it's taking me longer
than I expected.
Turns out I'm not
that good at sewing.
But it's the thought
that counts, isn't it?
You really love being
in that unit, huh?
Valkyrie, I mean.
I do, so I wish I was better.
I feel like I hold
them back sometimes.
But Big Bro Nazuna is perfect!
He can move exactly
the way Teach
tells him to every time!
That may be. But I
wonder if he's happy.
[KURO]
Is that all you wanted to say?
[KEITO]
Kiryu, wait.
If you want me to be
like everyone else,
that's not how I roll, man.
I'm guessing this means you're
in some kind of trouble.
[NAZUNA singing]
[sighs]
[KURO]
Hey! Yeah, you, shorty!
Hey, wait. Are you a girl?
Guess not. My bad.
Uh--
Think I know you.
You're the guy in
Itsuki's unit, right?
My name's Kiryu Kuro,
and I'm the one they
call a cheap thug.
Itsuki and I have
known each other
since we were little brats.
[gasps]
You gonna say anything? Huh?
Are you seriously gonna cry?
Come on. Man, I'm-- I'm sorry.
Huh? Oh, this? It's a
uniform for our school.
They asked me if I could
make an extra one.
Sewing is a talent of mine.
Itsuki's pretty good
at it, too, of course.
But my mom's the one who
taught us how to do it.
She'd give us lessons all
the time back in the day.
Before you go, can you pass on
a message to Itsuki for me?
Tell him he should be careful.
There's some shady
stuff goin' on.
[KURO] You both need to
look out for each other.
He's easy to misunderstand,
but trust me,
he's not a bad guy.
[KURO]
What's wrong with that kid?
Why's he bein' all quiet
and weird? Oh, right.
I wonder if it's because
his voice changed
since the last time
he sang with Valkyrie.
I mean, it didn't sound bad.
It was almost seductive.
His voice has that kind of
energy that draws people in.
At least to me. Maybe
Itsuki hasn't noticed.
[NAZUNA] It wasn't long after
that the concert system
endorsed by the
student council started
to make itself known.
"DreFes." A musical battle
where units compete
on the same stage to see
who's talent is stronger.
Those who were weak had
to leave the school.
And our group, Valkyrie,
was suddenly drawn into
the growing dramatics.
[SHU] Kind of unusual for you
to be awake during the day.
Is this a bad omen?
Are you trying to act
like an upperclassman?
If this was anyone else, I
would've hung up already, Rei.
fine? Tenshouin's boys?
I'm not worried about it--
they're no match for Valkyrie.
You can't make a performance pop
just by tossing cash at it.
The stage is where
artists like myself
showcase their sublime works.
Where I can offer up
my very essence
to the rest of the world.
That blueblood has no
right to the stage.
People shouldn't use
wealth to trespass
in a place that's
meant for true art.
After all, as idols, they're
only third-rate, right?
So dumb. Anyway,
I appreciate the warning.
I'm being careful, believe me.
You have a good night.
Thanks again.
[sighs]
[NAZUNA] As of right now,
we are still the top unit
of Yumenosaki Academy.
But if something doesn't change,
people are gonna lose
interest in Valkyrie soon.
Since we can only use
previous recordings
of my voice before it changed,
Valkyrie won't be able
to release any new songs.
There's also a limit to
the arrangements we can do.
[NAZUNA]
That's why...
...I need to train my new voice
until Teach will approve of it.
If he allows me to sing again,
then Valkyrie can continue
to grow and evolve.
We'll stay strong.
And, if that can happen for me,
then maybe there's
a chance that Teach
might start to see Mikachin
as more than just
a backup dancer.
He came to this school
because he wanted
to be an idol, just
like the rest of us.
For now, I might
just be the puppet
with a forgotten voice, but
I'll show him I can change.
I have to.
Hey Big Bro, Surprise!
I know it's already May, but
here's your birthday present!
So, happy late birthday!
I made it all by myself!
Thank you.
[MIKA] I know you're used to
wearing clothes made by Teach,
so this probably won't compare,
but tears were shed over it.
Those are padparadscha
sapphires.
[MIKA] The sapphire's your
birthstone, isn't it?
These ones are just
imitations, obviously.
But you can't tell
by looking at them.
I thought they'd be kind
of a good luck charm.
[NAZUNA]
Mika.
Huh?
[NAZUNA, crying]
I'm so--
Thank you. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
[MIKA]
I'm so sorry, Big Bro Nazuna!
Please forgive me!
[MIKA] I promise I didn't
mean to make you cry!
Are you feeling better?
[door clicks]
[SHU]
What's all the noise about?
Oh, you finally gave it to him?
Can't believe you had
the nerve to gift that
to someone as
a birthday present.
[SHU laughs]
I was trying to
hide it from you!
What gives? How'd you see?
I'm so embarrassed!
If you didn't want
anyone to see it,
then you shouldn't have
left it lying around
in such an obvious location.
You've no one to blame but
your own carelessness.
I know you're right, okay?
Aw... Now that I think about it,
there were times
when it looked like
someone else was
sewing it with me!
Oh, my gosh, it was
you, wasn't it?
It took you this long
to figure it out?
Did you think you had a fairy
godmother or something?
[MIKA] Aw! It was supposed
to be my birthday present
to Big Bro Nazuna,
and now it's ruined
because I didn't
actually make it myself!
This is all your fault!
That was so stupid, Teach!
--Stupid, stupid, stupid!
--[NAZUNA chuckles]
Hey look, he's smiling.
[gasps] I missed it!
It's because you were blocking
my line of vision, you idiot!
[MIKA]
I wasn't blockin' anything!
[SHU] Then how would you
describe what you were doing?
Nito! Did you really
smile for us?
Show it to me, one more time!
Come here.
Show me that beautiful
smile of yours!
I swear, it could
purify the world!
[SHU] Great. You're back to
your usual expressionless self!
This is your fault,
Kagehira! You did this!
As punishment, you can go
sell all of these tickets!
Wait, these are all for
our concert? For real?
We've never had to sell
our own tickets before.
Things change, don't they?
I'm not thrilled
about it either.
But we aren't always
going to be at the top,
so we need to learn how
to promote ourselves.
Sell every single one of those.
We need to show everyone
what it means to be idols.
Go on now. You'd better
get started soon.
[NAZUNA grunts]
I agree. Let's do it together!
All three of us.
Don't be an idiot! Let go!
A real artist doesn't
have to walk around town
begging to sell
his work! Unhand me!
[NAZUNA laughs]
[gasps]
[laughing]
Nito.
[gasps]
[MIKA]
Hurry, let's go!
[SHU]
You morons! Stop pulling me!
I'm the one who is
supposed to tell you
which way to move!
[NAZUNA]
I still remember that day.
It was nice and sunny,
with a refreshing breeze.
It felt good to
spend time outside.
We ended up selling tickets
to our concert all day,
until the sun went down.
I love looking back
and remembering a time
when Teach and Mikachin
were always by my side.
[CROWD chattering]
[CROWD cheers]
[NAZUNA] We were happy.
We hadn't realized yet
that a cruel time was
creeping up on us,
when the marionettes'
strings would be cut.