[SAGAMI]
Homeroom's officially over.
Congrats, everyone.
Summer break starts tomorrow.
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
But I guess it
doesn't really make
any difference for you guys.
That's the truth.
This summer feels completely
different than it did last year.
[MAKOTO] Maybe it's because
the revolution was a success,
but everyone seems
super motivated now!
[HOKUTO] Yeah. It's the
best time to level up,
if you think about it.
People in summer-only events
are hard at work in lessons.
And some people are working
part-time jobs at school, too.
As for us,
we're gonna be competing in
the SS and Trickstar's ready.
We're going above
and beyond for sure.
Yeah, we'll be representing
the whole academy!
--[SUBARU] Ukki!
--[MAKOTO yelps]
Don't let your nerves get
you all tensed up again!
Everything you said is true.
But, still, we can't forget:
it's supposed to be fun, right?
--[MAKOTO] Right!
--[HOKUTO] You bet!
[phone chimes]
[ANZU]
Huh?
Ah, summer vacation.
Here we are, a few days in.
Um, Hiyori?
Man, where are you?
And who else is it?
Oh, Sazanami?
Are either of you around?
[MAKOTO]
Hmm? Hey, hold on.
You're Aoba from
Switch, aren't you?
What on earth
are you doing here?
Ah, you're Yuuki from Trickstar.
Isn't it obvious?
I'm looking for these guys.
[MAKOTO] Oh, cool, is
this for the Summer Live?
[TSUMUGI] Yep. They asked me if
I would be their official guide.
We agreed to meet, but they're
late and nowhere to be found.
--[phone rings]
--[TSUMUGI] Oh.
Excuse me for a sec.
Yes, hello, there.
This Hiyori?
Hey, where are you? What?!
Is now really the time to
be stopping for baked goods?
[HIYORI]
There's no way I could resist.
Look, I'll head
straight to the academy.
No need to wait for me.
You can't just go wandering
around on your own like this!
I hope you know I haven't
forgotten the time
you ditched me and went
shopping all night long!
[phone beeps]
Huh?
[ANZU]
Two guesses where he went.
[MAKOTO]
Got enough?
Oh, wow, you're probably right.
Thank you for the tip!
Later. Good luck with that!
It's good to see you.
So where are you headed
with all of that bread?
[ANZU]
The theme park.
[MAKOTO]
Well, it is summer vacation!
Oh, it's for work.
See?
Huh? Since the recent
hero show your group put on
was so well received,
our theme park would like to
plan further events
featuring you.
We think a summer idol concert
will increase park visitors.
What do you guys
think about this?
[YUTA]
Let's do it!
Hey, Big Bro!
How would you feel about
leaving all the planning
for this one to me?
I mean, that depends.
Think you can do it?
Yeah, c'mon, trust me!
So, then, Sakuma,
can I be in charge of planning?
Yeah, sure, do
whatever you want.
[HINATA, YUTA chuckle]
Aw, yeah!
'Bout time 2wink went out there
and made a name for ourselves!
I have no business sticking
my nose into all that anyway.
I leave my beloved children
in your capable hands.
[YUTA, HINATA]
Hm-hm.
[REI]
Nap time.
[MAKOTO] Ah, that's why
you're going up there.
[ANZU]
Yep. So what're you doing?
Oh, I'm gonna head to
the school after this.
We're having a planning meeting
about the Summer Live
in a little bit.
Wait, the "Summer Live"?
Oh, no! Surely this
isn't the first
you're hearing of all that?
Uh, I have the proposal.
Let me just dig that out.
Ah! Found it!
[EICHI]
Good grief.
Always one to keep people
waiting, isn't that right?
Would you like a cup of tea?
No, thank you.
I have no way of knowing
what you might put in it.
There's no need
to be so on-guard.
I'm not your adversary
this time, after all.
[HOKUTO grunts]
I genuinely want to
help you out, I promise!
That's the reason I planned
the Summer Live to begin with--
to give you all some extra
practice for the upcoming SS.
Competing against another
school's powerhouse
will do just that, right?
I do wonder what's keeping
Hiyori. He's so late.
I haven't heard the slightest
peep from Tsumugi, either.
Wait, Hiyori?
[EICHI] Yes, you're
going to be performing
with him at the Summer Live.
Perhaps you remember him?
He's was once a
Yumenosaki Academy student.
[HOKUTO]
Hmm?
[EICHI] And one of the former
fine's two star performers.
Tomoe Hiyori.
Don't tell me
you've forgotten him.
Huh, Masked Hokke?
[gasps]
Oh, I see.
So this is what their
unit is called, then?
Eve is a good name.
[EICHI]
Yes.
And they're an integral
part of the group
expected to win the SS.
A group called Eden.
They're a masterpiece, honestly.
[ANZU]
Huh?
The two groups are called
Adam and Eve by themselves,
but they're called Eden when
they combine into one group!
It's kinda awesome, actually.
They're like a giant robot!
Eden is Trickstar's most
formidable opponent, for sure.
But for the Summer Live, only
the two from Eve are coming--
not all four of them.
So it's really just
a joint concert?
Yeah, that's why I'm not
quite as nervous about it.
--[JUN] Hey.
--Huh?
I'm talkin' to you, four-eyes.
Uh, yes, sir, I'm sorry!
Is there some way
I can be of help to you?
Some way you can
be of help to me...
I think that should be obvious.
After all, we are dealing
with money here.
Are you trying to rob me
or something, mister?
--[JUN sighs]
--[yelps]
Actually, it's kinda
like the opposite.
Huh? Is that my wallet? Ah!
[JUN] Calm down. Ya dropped
it earlier, that's all.
I picked it up. You want
it back, don't'cha?
Thank you. I really
appreciate that.
[sighs]
You got all freaked out.
Am I that intimidating?
I would never do anything bad,
Yuuki Makoto of Trickstar.
How do you know my
name and my group?
[ANZU gasps]
[MAKOTO gasps]
Are you a member of Eden?
Or, hold on, more
specifically, you're in Eve!
[JUN] That's right.
My name's Sazanami Jun.
Nice to meet ya.
I see how it is, though.
You haven't done much
research about us, have you?
And I took time out of my busy
schedule to come down here.
[MAKOTO] Why's this guy
in such a bad mood?
Is he like this all the time?
--[phone buzzes]
--[JUN] Hm?
Oh. 'Course Ohiisan
would call me now.
I guess I'll be
seeing ya around.
Yeah, yeah, whaddaya want?
Man, I'm still in shock.
[giggles]
[game music plays]
[MAKOTO]
If I'm not mistaken,
Eden sings the theme for that
game in their combined form.
You have researched.
Kinda.
I was in the Game Research
Club so, yes, technically.
It's one of the more
relaxed, easy-going clubs.
I still pop in occasionally.
There used to be this one guy
in it--an amazing upperclassman.
You could even
call him legendary.
Rumor is, that upperclassman
is actually the one
who developed this game.
Would it be cool if
I gave it a quick try?
[ANZU]
Sure!
[MAKOTO laughing]
Fantastic!
Here goes nothin'!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Welcome, Challenger!
[JUN] Hey! Are you
playing as yourself?
[MAKOTO gasps]
No one would know it
by the way you look,
but you've got some guts.
It's just a coincidence.
I didn't pick me, I swear!
Well, I gladly
accept the challenge.
Let's do this, then.
It's almost like we're being
forced onto the same path
by the hands of destiny!
--[JUN] Heh!
--[ANNOUNCER A] Round one!
What kind of fate have the
gods pressed upon me now?
[ANNOUNCER A]
Fight!
[EICHI]
Listen, Hokuto.
Even if it's motivated
by hostility or hate,
you must make
sure Eve's serious,
and you'd better make it
happen by the Summer Live.
[HOKUTO]
Hmm.
That way we'll see
how to beat Eden,
even if we only
know about one half.
I get it.
So that's the whole
purpose of this concert.
--[gasps]
--[HIYORI] Gentlemen!
[HIYORI]
I'm so sorry for my tardiness.
Consider this my formal apology.
I'm the one you've
been waiting for.
You know who I am.
Eve's Tomoe Hiyori!
It's been so long,
my dear Eichi!
I'm glad to see
you're still alive.
I don't quite believe
you're sincere.
[HIYORI]
Ah, well, I don't care.
I'm no longer in
fine, after all.
Therefore, you're not
someone who matters to me
in one way or another anymore!
Now you've upset me.
How callous.
Where's Tsumugi, by the way?
[HIYORI]
Oh, him?
I requested that he carry
my luggage to the hotel.
[TSUMUGI] This guy even
brought his pet, Bloody Mary.
[TSUMUGI] Hiyori just does
whatever he wants, doesn't he?
[BLOODY MARY barks]
Well, I suppose it's no matter.
Thanks for accepting
our invitation
to participate in
the Summer Live.
Now, Hokuto, introduce yourself.
[HOKUTO gasps]
It's nice to meet you.
At least, I think.
I'm here representing Trickstar.
Hidaka Hokuto.
[HIYORI]
Hm?
Oh, yes, I have heard about you!
Although you guys didn't
seem very interesting,
so I didn't research you much.
All I can say is that I hope
you'll all do your best
serving as the heel
to our stardom!
At least you better, Trickstar.
Poor Hokuto.
Do you think he's
gonna be all right?
Hey, question!
If you're not gonna eat that,
you think I could have it?
I'm carb-loading to
store up some energy!
I think that you're energetic
enough, but yeah, okay.
Thanks for that!
I wanna have so much pizazz
I shine brighter than
the midsummer sun!
And I don't just mean sparkle.
I wanna be blazing!
[REI] That kind of fire
is all right for you,
but I, for one,
don't like the heat.
I find it exhausting.
[groaning]
Uh, Sakuma, sir?
The air conditioner in my
coffin is on the fritz lately,
so I came here in search
of cooler temperatures.
I'm still hot.
But on another note,
don't you two have a joint
lesson with Eve this afternoon?
Don't eat too much or your
lunch is going to come back up.
Uh, huh?
Wait, how did you
know about that?
Haven't you realized by
now that I know everything
there is to know about
Yumenosaki Academy?
So, um, could you maybe
give us some information?
[REI]
Hm?
Would you happen to know
anything about that group Eve?
Tomoe, one of their members,
used to be a student
here at Yumenosaki Academy.
I tried doing some research
on him in the records room.
But I couldn't find
anything on him at all.
Seriously?
Looking for an inside
scoop on your rival?
You must be nervous.
I can't help it.
If you really want to know more,
then I would go
talk to Sakasaki.
He's persistent when it
comes to gathering information.
Particularly when there's
been some sort of cover-up.
But he's so busy.
All Natsume has time for
is his fortune-telling work.
I barely even
see him these days.
It'll be hard, then.
We've got our work
cut out for us.
[REI sighs]
[HIYORI] Here!
I'm officially turning in Eve's
side of the plans
for the Summer Live!
We insist that you move
exactly as we instruct you to.
That wasn't the deal!
It's a joint concert.
We should plan together!
[HIYORI]
Uh-huh, yeah, sure, sure.
I'm so happy to know
that's how you feel!
But guess what?
If we were to work
down on your level,
we'd end up looking subpar,
and I can't have that.
[HOKUTO gasps]
[HIYORI] I, Tomoe Hiyori,
will not tolerate mediocrity.
Eve must never participate in
a run-of-the-mill, dull show,
for we are spectacular!
[HOKUTO]
Hmm...
Don't you dare look at me.
I can't be of any
help to you here.
[HOKUTO groans]
Negotiate with persistence.
It's your job to convince them
that Trickstar can be
beneficial in some way.
But if you're not careful,
he'll use you till
there's nothing left.
[HOKUTO]
Tomoe, sir!
[HIYORI]
Oh? Hidaka?
That's your name, yes?
I thought you looked
familiar somehow.
Aren't you our teacher,
Mr. Hidaka's son?
Your teacher?
[HIYORI]
He is your dad, right?
He's incredibly busy
with his career as an idol,
but he still finds
the time to drop by
Reimei Academy to teach.
[HOKUTO] Even though Yumenosaki
Academy is his alma mater,
he teaches at its rival school.
Which means that you, literally
the son of a former top idol,
will perform with his students.
Perform?
No, I think the SS will be
more like a fight to the death.
[HOKUTO grunts]
Well, we were bound
to compete someday.
But that would just be
a major pain, so no thanks!
I only want to think positively!
I seek out that which is pure
and essential to my own success!
That's ideal,
the perfect Hiyori!
Sorry, I don't get it.
I suppose it's inevitable, then.
If we must compete,
we'll give our all.
And we will surely win.
I have no doubt.
[HIYORI]
I almost forgot!
I brought some lovely quiches!
I got so many different kinds,
why don't we
enjoy them together?
Eichi, how about
a nice pot of tea?
Oh, and the salmon is
my absolute favorite,
so don't get any ideas.
I will not share!
Yes, of course. As you
like it, right, Hiyori?
[HOKUTO]
What's with this guy?
Is he for real?
But he's a former fine
member, so it makes sense.
[MAKOTO] Man, I guess
I got really into it!
Ya know, you're more aggressive
than I would've expected.
Oh, really? That's funny.
You're a lot more polite
than I would've guessed.
Did you call me polite?
Guilty.
Our school's pretty serious
about proper decorum,
so if you're not polite, you
get singled out very quickly.
This other guy in
my group, Ohiisan,
I guess you could call
him a handful. [sighs]
I'm basically at his
beck and call 24/7.
Today felt almost like
a vacation from all that.
I could relax.
Heh. Hey, listen, I'm sorry
for actin' weird earlier.
No sweat! It turned
out great in the end!
And, well, I'm glad I
could be of help somehow.
Yeah, you really were.
Ya know, it's not very
often that I play games.
He told me to play a little
and then post about it
on social media and stuff.
But you made it more fun.
Oh, so you mean you were doing
that to help with publicity?
Good for you! That's
what I call commitment!
[MAKOTO]
What a relief.
I was a little unsure
of him at first.
But I think we'll
get along just fine.
[ANZU] Meanwhile,
over at the theme park.
[BOTH]
Here we go!
I hope we can get along!
Yeah, I hope so, too!
Who would have thought?
I can't believe
we got the chance
to do a concert
here with Ra*bits!
Oh, wow, so sweet and delicious!
Here, try it, Tomoya.
Ahh.
This makes me feel
a little bit awkward.
Why? Nothing weird here.
Hurry, before it melts.
That's so good!
Quick, you try it!
[TOMOYA, HAJIME gasp]
Wow!
[TOMOYA] Aw, man.
You ate almost the whole thing.
Your unit gets along so well.
It's really nice.
Well, 2wink seems to be
just as close as they are.
I mean, you are twins.
[YUTA]
I guess.
But it gets old sometimes,
how Big Bro always accepts
gigs that sell us as a twin act.
We even did a live
performance recently
that had us doing a silly
"cloning technique."
[laughs] I guess 2wink
has its share of troubles.
If we keep coasting
on the twin thing,
we won't reach
our full potential.
That's it!
At the next concert,
I'm gonna open a whole
new frontier for 2wink!
That's right, Yuta.
And as your brother,
I'll be rooting for you
every step of the way.
Hey, want some bread?
Big Sis went out of her way
to bring it here to all of us!
[HINATA]
Thanks, but no thanks!
You okay?
Is something the matter?
I was just wondering
if Jin Sagami is around.
Are you a big fan
of Mister Sagami's?
He retired from idol
life a while back.
But he was one of the
top idols for a long time!
Oh!
Hey, you two, what's up?
Ukki! Oh, uh, and
who's that with you?
He's Sazanami Jun, from Eve.
I happened to run into him
in front of the station.
[JUN]
Hi, nice to meet you.
[SUBARU laughs]
Same to you!
Our joint lesson is gonna
be in here, isn't it?
[MAO]
Yeah, supposedly.
But I don't think we
should interrupt right now.
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
[HOKUTO]
Something feels off.
Like he's trying to
mess me up on purpose.
And also, this choreography is
supposed to be for four people,
but here I am,
dancing all alone.
It'll look weird,
like something's missing.
Does dancing alone
always feel so bad?
I can tell just by watching.
Trickstar uses their
friendship as a crutch, huh?
[HOKUTO grunts]
If you can't stand on your own,
then you'll be a failure,
no matter what you do!
[HOKUTO gasps]
Not that you can help it.
You're still in the process
of evolving as a performer,
so I'll cut you some slack.
[HOKUTO] He adjusted
my movement while dancing
and didn't miss a beat!
So here's to unity!
And to teamwork!
The power of friendship!
Those words sound
beautiful when said aloud,
but there's nothing more
hideous than weak creatures
turning into parasites
of one another.
And you'll find no
greater meaning than when
each individual member strives
to be the best
version of themselves!
[HOKUTO] He's eccentric,
to say the least,
but he does have a point.
And, besides, his performance
hasn't lost energy,
even though he's been talking.
The direction of his body
and gaze, his presence--
his entire being is reaching
toward the audience.
This is Tomoe Hiyori's world!
Is this what the former star
players of fine are like?
It's no wonder they made it to
the top of Yumenosaki Academy.
What's the matter?
Come at me with
everything you've got!
Whether you're an underling
or just a side character,
I don't discriminate.
If you're onstage, I'll make
sure to use you efficiently.
Do your best! Do your worst!
Come on, Trickstar!
Hokke isn't the only member
of Trickstar, ya know!
Whoopsie!
--[SUBARU yelling]
--[crash]
You've got lots of energy!
Akehoshi, are you all right?
Jun, you're late!
How dare you?
I cannot believe that you
forced me, your superior,
to break into enemy
territory all by myself!
What on earth were
you thinking?!
If I remember correctly,
you're the one who ditched me,
because you went shopping
and lost track of time.
And this isn't enemy territory.
We came here to work, remember?
You should be on your best
behavior, in my opinion,
Ohiisan.
Are we all finally here?
Then now's the time.
[SUBARU]
Mm?
Let's start the lesson
after we do one song.
[HIYORI, JUN]
Hmm?
[HOKUTO]
Tomoe.
You're about to witness
Trickstar's real potential,
now that all four
of us are together.
Take notes, and feel free
to point out anything
that doesn't meet
your standards.
We're not so weak that
we'll allow ourselves
to be destroyed by our
own refusal to evolve.
We'll make you recognize that
we're equals and colleagues!
We'll compete,
even if we're up against
the reigning top idol group.
[HIYORI] Heh. You're
acting so much tougher
now that your three friends
are here to back you up.
I'm dying to see your
true abilities, Trickstar!
Show me what you've got!
Now, we'll sing! All together!
I want to see your love! I want
to feel the love in your music!
[ANZU] Meanwhile, in a place
yet unknown to the rest of us.
[applause]
What did ya think, Leo?
How was it?
Do you feel a little better now?
I do.
Thank you for that, Mikeji Mama.
For a genius like me to not
present my new composition,
and instead waste
my time on pranks
is a huge loss for
the entire world!
[LEO laughing]