[ANZU] We were all so
certain that Trickstar
had been permanently separated.
But then Yuuki and Isara
found their way back.
And the three of them performed
together at the DDD.
[ANZU] As for Hidaka, It looks
like he will be joining
Tenshouin's unit, fine.
[CROWD]
Trickstar!
[ANZU] Will we ever see all
four members of Trickstar
together on stage again?
[WATARU]
Hokuto!
It's Hibiki Wataru!
So good to hear from you!
No one called you,
you Masked Pervert!
Ah! That's not the
only way I'll appear!
[WATARU]
Hm.
It's not worth it.
I don't have the time or energy
to deal with you right now.
Amazing!
I have a hard time believing
you're that tired, though.
For one thing, you
didn't even bother
to perform with
the others today.
[SORA] Woo-hoo! Hey, are you
guys seeing what I'm seeing?
It's a blimp!
So cool!
How strange that it just
came out of nowhere.
Hey, Master, is this
what magic looks like?
Yes. Every move a magician makes
results in some kind
of magic. Just watch.
[TSUMUGI] Yeah, seems like
he's just as over the top
and out there, as usual.
Wait, is that Hidaka with him?
[NATSUME]
It appears to be. Makes sense.
There's a rumor out there
that he's planning to
transfer to fine soon.
Is he?
If so, then that means Eichi
must really believe in him.
How can you say that
when it's so obvious
he's just trying
to weaken Trickstar?
Even if that was the case,
Eichi recognizes his talent.
It sounds like you're
speaking from experience.
Is that how it was?
Y'know, before all this.
When you were a member of fine?
Oh, not at all.
It wasn't really
like that for me.
I hope he's well.
I still think about him.
[EICHI]
Thank you so much.
We appreciate your support.
[ANZU] At the time,
I still had no idea.
But of course,
I'd find out later
that Tenshouin had his own
hidden feelings and agendas.
--[thud]
--[TSUMUGI yelps]
[ANZU]
One year ago, everything about
Yumenosaki Academy
was different.
Things weren't like
they are now.
Can I ask you something?
[STUDENT 10A] Anyway,
I get that he's desperate,
but he didn't have to be
so pathetic over a class.
[STUDENT 10B]
He works hard. Who cares?
[STUDENT 10C]
Yeah, what does...
[EICHI] That's not going to be
enough to change the school!
[KEITO] We have to take
time to carefully lay out
all of the instructions--
[EICHI] No we don't, Keito.
We have to find something
that inspires them
to demand change!
And then we need everyone
to move at once!
[KEITO]
Aoba?
I'm so sorry. I didn't
mean to interrupt.
Ah, no worries.
We were just
talking about school.
[TSUMUGI] That's not what
it looked like to me.
I'm sorry to make you come
all the over way here to get it.
But here's the list
of books we have.
Thanks so much.
I feel bad having you reorganize
that list by yourself.
Let me know if I can help.
It's no problem, I promise.
[EICHI]
I see, so you and Keito Hasumi
are both on the
library committee?
I can't believe he's
come up with a reason
for you to do so
much by yourself.
It's fine, he's busy running
the student council.
Let me help you. Say when.
Wow, that would be great!
Wait, you shouldn't
have to do that.
You just got out
of the hospital!
Yeah, but I can still
help out a little bit.
[TSUMUGI] You and Keito
have known each other
since you were kids, right?
[EICHI]
That is true.
But it's like I have his
phone number or anything.
[TSUMUGI]
Interesting.
Actually, we went to Hasumi's
family temple for consultation.
My grandfather's about
to pass and they've done
our funerals for generations.
We've got a long history.
I see.
[EICHI] When I got there,
for some reason,
we started talking about
the future of the school.
[TSUMUGI]
What's going on with it?
[EICHI] The value of this
school in the entertainment
industry is declining.
When we tried to find the cause,
there was only one
conclusion we could reach.
[REI]
Hey there, Tsumugi.
[TSUMUGI]
Rei? I thought you transferred
to the sister school
in New York?
Yeah, I did,
but I just got back.
I leave for Shanghai tomorrow.
Man, I can't keep up
with your global lifestyle.
Neither can I!
I have no idea what's
going on at school.
Catch me up when we
get a chance to talk.
[TSUMUGI]
Absolutely!
Sorry to interrupt.
You're fine.
Okay.
Guess that means you're
friends with Sakuma Rei, too?
Yeah, sure. He's still someone
I admire and respect very much.
So, can you tell me
what you discovered?
What caused the school
to change so much?
[EICHI] The cause isn't
worth dwelling on.
What's important is changing
the way the school is now.
And in order to do that,
we have to be proactive,
so Hasumi and I
came up with a plan.
[TSUMUGI]
Oh.
[EICHI] We'd take three
people who represent
Yumenosaki Academy,
and then place them
high above everyone else.
Patterned after the
"Three Deities"
of Japanese mythology,
the "Three Eccentrics."
What a cool name.
And at least we'll know exactly
who's representing us
in the industry.
I think it makes a lot of sense.
We've already decided
who they are.
Wataru Hibiki as Amaterasu,
Kanata Shinkai as Susanoo,
and Rei Sakuma as Tsukuyomi.
[TSUMUGI]
All three of them fit perfectly!
Rei really has adopted
the character of Tsukuyomi,
god of the night.
He can't stand the sun.
But that could also
be a problem.
They might fit too well.
I want to create a tear to
find out who they really are.
Um, what do you mean?
Make a tear?
Don't you think they'd
be more appealing?
I think I understand.
In that case, why
don't we find a way
to add a few more people?
[EICHI] I was just thinking
the exact same thing.
What do you think of
the "Five Eccentrics"?
[TSUMUGI]
"Five Eccentrics."
If there's a larger
cast of characters,
then the importance of each
individual is lessened.
I have a question.
Actually, it's more of a favor.
[TSUMUGI]
What is it?
You seem to know
a lot of people, right?
This would go a lot
quicker if we could
use your connections.
[TSUMUGI]
Wait.
I feel like you're asking
me to do something scary.
[laughs] I hope not.
But would you be able
to suggest two people
to create the Five Eccentrics?
If you're just wanting two,
I think I could probably
help with that.
Let me think for a sec.
First one that comes
to mind is Shu Itsuki
based on how polished Valkyrie's
performances always are.
Then for the second one...
--[beeping]
--What is that sound?
They call it an "Eichi Gauge."
My doctor put it on me.
It stays silent as long
as it can detect movement.
When it starts getting
close to zero,
it notifies someone at home
and I'm retrieved whether
I like it or not.
As expected for
the son of a large
financial conglomerate.
I bet they really love you.
[EICHI] It's not love, they
just don't want anything
to happen to their
precious successor.
They couldn't care less
about me as a person.
Anyway, I have to go.
But can I point something
out to you first?
Several volumes in the
collection that pertain
to specific fields
seem to be missing.
[TSUMUGI]
What? Seriously?
I bet some students
forgot to return them
before they graduated.
[EICHI] There's quite
a large number missing,
so I doubt it's something
as simple as that.
If I had to guess,
I'd say they're hidden
somewhere in a secret room.
But where would
a secret room be?
I know where everything is.
Anyway, will you keep me posted?
About the other Eccentrics.
Right! Yes.
Thank you, Eichi. Call you soon.
Yeah, I'm walking toward
the front gate now.
Please tell me you're not coming
to get me in a limousine.
Because I don't want to draw
that kind of attention.
[sighs]
[WATARU] "And though
you try to plow through
all the deception
and seek pleasure,
you did not know that the
pleasure you were seeking
was no more than deception."
[EICHI]
Hibiki's just so beautiful.
[WATARU] "When you
forgot me, your soul..."
[EICHI] It's like he's wrapped
in a mysterious brilliance.
[gasps]
[EICHI] He's still so far.
I can't reach him.
But I promise I will fill in
the unbearable distance--
The gap between high and low.
[EICHI]
I will get to you one day,
no matter what I have
to do to get there.
[REI]
A secret room? Yeah. I guess so.
It's a basement stack room.
For real? That's awesome!
It might be a little
hard to find, but,
I know it's in the very
back of the reference room.
Thank you so much!
I knew if anyone would know
what I was talking about,
it would be you!
[REI]
Heads up.
Whoops-a-daisy!
Uh... Is this really the
key to the secret room?
But why?
It just felt right.
[TSUMUGI]
Okay. You're so confusing to me.
[REI] Well, I'm off
to Shanghai. Take care.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Be careful out there.
Tsumugi.
[TSUMUGI]
Yes?
[REI]
Don't spend all your energy
doing things for other
people. Believe in yourself.
You can do anything if you try.
[TSUMUGI]
You're the only one who's
ever said that about me.
It means more than you know.
[TSUMUGI]
There really is a secret room.
So many books that
don't look like
they were ever checked
in to the library.
Like these.
They look like
classified documents.
They smell like danger.
[TSUMUGI] Now there really
is a strange smell.
Seems like it's coming
from behind this door?
[VOICE screams]
[NATSUME] Abracadabra.
And a little hocus-pocus.
There!
[TSUMUGI]
Huh?
What are you doing here?
And more importantly,
who let you into
this secret room?
Talkin' to you, Aoba Tsumugi.
I don't think I ever
told you my name.
[NATSUME]
You're so responsible and always
working so hard,
I should learn from you.
Even if you don't
work like a slave,
everyone loves you.
Now that is a recipe
I've been dying to learn.
C'mon, stop!
I'm not like,
famous or anything.
Odd. Guess my magic
wasn't strong enough.
Well, it's obvious
I need more training.
Master is not going to be proud.
Wait a minute, I think
I may have heard about you.
[NATSUME]
I'm sure.
I am the magician
of Yumenosaki Academy,
Sakasaki Natsume.
And for a nominal
fee, I will make
every stress and worry
you have disappear.
[TSUMUGI]
Uh.
[NATSUME chuckles]
[TSUMUGI grunts]
What the...?
I think I know you.
Don't you remember me, Natsume?
[NATSUME]
Hm?
[TSUMUGI] Your mother's a
famous fortuneteller, right?
Yes, but everyone knows that.
I'm not sure what
you're trying to prove.
When you were a kid,
you liked to wear girls'
clothes, didn't you?
What?!
I'm Sakasaki Natsume.
You can call me
Little Namie! Hi there!
Not that it even
matters, but yes,
I was made to act like
a girl when I was little!
You were also going
to a dance school
at that time, weren't you?
I think I did, but
just for a few weeks.
I assume you're talking
about the shady one?
With the bad management?
[laughs] That was
managed by my mother.
Awkward.
But I remember her
coming to my mom
about some trouble
she was having.
She couldn't pay the fee,
so she waived
my monthly tuition.
I remember that was a pain.
Mom always talks
about the little girl
dance prodigy and how
beautiful she was.
You're basically like
a hometown legend.
Yeah thanks, I remember now.
Please stop telling that story.
Now that I think about it,
there was a mean little
boy at the school, too.
He was called
Big Brother Tsumugi.
That was you, wasn't it?
For what it's worth,
you seem different.
[TSUMUGI] After that, my
parents filed for bankruptcy,
divorced, and remarried.
A lot has changed since then.
Yeah. That must've
been pretty rough.
I'm glad we got to see
each other again,
Little Namie.
[NATSUME]
The next time you call me that,
I will turn your face
into a hideous mess,
but I won't use magic to do it.
Okay, please stop!
[TSUMUGI] What kind of
experiment are you doing?
Nothin' much, just killin' time.
Seeing what different
elements can do.
Master likes to practice
fantastical magic.
But I'm more into
alchemy and sorcery.
The classics, ya know?
That's so cool!
It looks just like
fairytale magic!
It "looks like" magic,
because that's what it is.
But it's not a fairytale.
Show's over. Time for you to go.
'Kay, if you say so.
Can I stop by here
again sometime?
Maybe we reconnected after
so long for a reason?
I'd like to try to be
friends if you would?
You're sort of a little
weirdo, aren't you,
Big Brother Tsumugi?
That's fine, but we can't
be like, best friends.
If a normal person like you
associates too closely
with magicians, you'll end up
miserable and unhappy.
Got it! Later!
[NATSUME laughs] He has no
idea what I'm talking about.
[EICHI coughs]
[EICHI] There are still so many
things I need to get done.
My body is fighting me.
[WATARU]
I'm very sorry, Hidaka Hokuto.
But it's like I told you before,
you have the dignified looks
required to play a prince.
But you have no
talent for acting.
Makeup and masks only go so far.
Therefore, I cannot
allow you to join
the theater club. I'm sorry.
I understand.
And I believe I've
uncovered your real game.
You said that just
to see how I'd react?
No, that was my
actual criticism.
[groans]
[door clicks]
Hi, can I help you?
Did you come here
to talk to me?
Or were you looking for Hokuto?
No, uh. Please excuse me.
[panting]
[EICHI]
My heart's still pounding.
Right now, I may be just
another random student to him.
But, if you give me a chance,
I can open your eyes.
I will carve my existence
into your heart, Hibiki.
It won't be long now.
The pathway is clear.
[TSUMUGI]
Eichi! Hey, Eichi?
Hey. What's up?
Everything all right?
I just found the perfect one!
The fifth person for
the Five Eccentrics.
His name is Sakasaki Natsume
and he's a first year!
I just talked to him for a
little while and I'm sure of it!
He's exactly what you want
at the top of this school.
You'd love him!
Okay.
Well, I'm convinced,
let's reach out.
[TSUMUGI]
Oh. Really? That's it?
You don't have to think
it over for a few days?
If he made that big of
an impression on you,
he must be exceptional.
I trust you.
I'm sure he won't disappoint!
Thank you!
No, I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
While you're here,
there's something else
I wanted to ask of you.
[TSUMUGI]
Uh?
[EICHI]
I want to make an idol unit.
I've always wanted friends
to chase my dream with.
I was wondering if you
would help me find
the perfect members to join?
I'd love to!
[STUDENT 10D]
The Five Eccentrics are so cool,
aren't they?
[STUDENT 10E] Don't you wish
we could be like them?
[STUDENT 10F] I could never
put on a concert like that.
They're so talented!
[STUDENT 10G] Who the hell
are these "Five Eccentrics"?
[STUDENT 10H] The school
is pushing them extra hard.
[STUDENT 10I] They're making
it impossible for us
to ever have a chance.
It's not fair!
[TSUMUGI]
It's so amazing.
Everyone in school's
talking about
the Five Eccentrics right now.
It seems like everything is
going according to your plan.
Don't forget, you had a lot
to do with this success, too.
Nice work.
And Sakasaki Natsume was
a wonderful recommendation.
[TSUMUGI] Giving a few
names is hardly anything.
But um, I was just wondering.
Is this what you wanted?
[EICHI]
What do you mean?
I feel like they
could be doing more.
From what I've seen,
the Five Eccentrics
aren't really leading the
school in a good direction.
It's the opposite.
Students seem to be
losing motivation.
I think it's okay.
We're still just
at the beginning.
This journey's long.
It'll be a while before
we see changes.
[TSUMUGI] Well, in the
meantime, have some tea.
I'd love to.
[TSUMUGI] By the way,
how is putting together
your new unit coming along?
It's going quite well, actually.
Your list had several
fine candidates.
And I had some good interviews
with a couple of them.
What? Out of the entire list?
You interviewed Ran Nagisa
and Tomoe Hiyori?
[EICHI]
Why? Should I not have?
[TSUMUGI] Oh! I'm sorry,
it's nothing like that,
they're both extremely talented.
I wouldn't have put them
on the list otherwise.
I'm just surprised.
But they're also, um...
How do I say this? A little hard
to handle in their own ways.
[EICHI] Ah. Yeah, I can
definitely see that.
Especially Ran. He just
seems difficult in general.
I can't believe you
convinced him at all.
How did you manage that?
Full frontal attack.
I explained that it'd be a
step up for him as an idol,
and suggested a possible
partnership with him
and our family businesses.
I thought about offering cash,
but then realized
it wasn't necessary.
[laughs] That's such a different
world from what I know
and it's making me dizzy
trying to understand.
Well, even if you're
finished gathering
the contracts, I think
it'll take a lot of time
and work to bring
everyone together.
Make sure you're not
pushing yourself too hard.
I think I'll be all right.
Because of a certain member.
I've chosen him to
help me with that.
So now, I should probably ask
if you'll be the
mediator for my unit?
What?
You're talking about me?
But what do I know
about any of this?
I forgot to tell you.
I found out some information.
I now know why the school's
value is declining.
[TSUMUGI]
Okay?
[EICHI] It's because of the
way this school is run.
Only those with exceptional
talent stand out,
and those without
it are forgotten.
Wow.
[EICHI] My goal is to make
a point with this unit.
That even if you
aren't prodigies like
the Five Eccentrics, you
can still shine like them.
No, you can shine more than them
if you're willing to work.
We have to make changes
and overhaul the system.
In order to do that,
we'll have to move
in a lot of
different directions.
That's why I wanted to ask you.
I need someone suitable
to represent this unit.
[gasps]
[EICHI] And someday, we will
defeat the Five Eccentrics.
Huh?
I meant to say.
I hope we'll be good
enough to surpass them.
That's my goal.
But I can't do it alone.
I need you, Tsumugi.
What do you say?
[TSUMUGI]
I say let's do it.
I would love to work
on this with you
and be a partner in
pursuing your dream.
I'm grateful. That means a lot.
[EICHI]
We'll be a good team.
Let's bring a revolution
to this Academy.
[EICHI]
Our unit will be called fine,
and we will put
an end to an era.