[ANZU]
Welcome to Yumenosaki Academy.
The name means "academy
where dreams bloom,"
and that's the goal
for all the students
who attend school here.
What is your dream?
Are you the next celebrity idol?
An actor? Or maybe a singer?
[ANZU]
Right now the production course
is still in development.
[phone chimes]
[SAGAMI] I'm Mr. Sagami,
your homeroom teacher.
Please come to the staff room
in the Idol department
before class starts.
[BOTH yelp]
[MAO]
Come on, you guys!
"You guys?" That was Hokke!
You're so rude! I was
doing my part right.
It seems you're the only
one who doesn't know
the choreography, yet. Akehoshi.
Huh? Yes I do!
"Step, bam, on the floor!"
Then "whee" around!
Then "sparkle," smile!
Don't speak with sound effects.
Especially when I explained
things to you so logically.
Hey, guys, you don't
have to fight about it.
Oh, crap.
Hate to bail, but I gotta
head back to my own classroom.
I forgot that I have class duty!
Wow, is that the time?
Hah! The minutes fly when
you're having fun, don't they?
--[HOKUTO growls]
--[SUBARU] Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
[ANZU gasps]
[MAO]
It's a girl.
What're you doing in
an idol course classroom?
Uh--
Wait, that's right.
I've heard about you.
Hello there!
You're the transfer student
people're talking about!
[BOYS]
Welcome to Yumenosaki!
Where dreams come true!
[HOKUTO] People have
been talking about you
for quite a while.
Mr. Sagami, our homeroom
teacher mentioned that
you're in the Production Course
that was established
recently, but...
...unfortunately there aren't
any classrooms for you yet.
Huh?
Hopefully they'll
be available soon.
But for now, you'll
be able to attend
some of the idol courses
with us for credit.
Consider yourself a temporary
member of class 2-A.
The three of us
are your classmates.
Just you?
Uh, sorry, you guys.
I gotta get to class duty.
Thanks for handling
the clean up!
So hey, uh... [chuckles]
What's your name, newbie?
[ANZU]
I'm Anzu.
That's great! My name's
Akehoshi Subaru!
Nice to meet you!
Let's be friends!
Sorry about him.
I'm Hidaka Hokuto, the class
representative for Class 2-A.
Our homeroom teacher
instructed me to look after you.
His name's Hokuto, but
you can call him "Hokke"!
Oh! And that one with the
glasses is Yuuki Makoto,
so call him "Ukki!"
There's more to me
than glasses, you know.
But I guess it's fine. Uh, hi!
Maybe they'll make
me memorable, Right?
Yes, my name is Yuuki Makoto,
and... I'm glad you're here.
[ANZU]
It's nice to meet you all.
Uh! I'm sorry I'm so nervous.
I'm just not very
experienced with girls.
[coughs] Right.
Since our school specializes
in training only
male idol groups,
it can feel a lot like
attending an all-boys academy.
I imagine being surrounded by
so many boys might be difficult.
But I'm here to make
you feel comfortable.
Same thing goes for these guys.
[SUBARU]
Mm-Hm!
That's right.
Happy to get to know you,
transfer student.
--Likewise, thank you.
--[door clicks]
[SAGAMI]
Ah, there you are.
[gasps]
Well, now I know why you never
stopped by the staff room.
Hey, Mr. Sagami.
You're her teacher,
you should be the one
keeping track of her, right?
Yeah! Way to neglect
your new students, teach!
Akehoshi!
Sorry about that.
Here are your textbooks
and some other supplies.
[ANZU]
Thanks!
Go ahead and take that
seat over... [groans]
C'mon, you guys.
I'm glad you're working hard.
But don't forget
to put those back.
[ALL gasp]
Right!
[ANZU chuckles]
[bell rings]
[KOGA]
Heh!
[SUBARU] Man, seemed like
everyone was having
an "off" day today!
Maybe we should invite those
guys to practice with us?
Sure. So, how was class
for you, transfer student?
Huh? Um...
If there's anything
you don't get,
feel free to ask Ukki!
Right? Right?
What? Why ask me?
Both of you are way
smarter than I--
Wait! You're making fun of me!
Give me a second
to find a comeback
that'll totally burn you!
Okay! You have until
I count to 100!
One, three, 20, 100!
What? That was way too fast!
Is it possible for
you two to stay quiet
for at least 30 seconds?
Hey, Akehoshi, How's
ten yen for your silence?
Wha--? No way?
Master Hokuto!
I'm your faithful doggy!
[MAKOTO] Wait, You let him
buy you for ten yen?
I can't help it! Look how
shiny and sparkly it is!
Uh...
You okay, transfer student?
Did you have a question
you wanted to ask?
I do, actually.
[SUBARU]
Mm-hm?
I was just wondering,
where we're going.
[HOKUTO clears throat]
Sorry. Since we're
on our lunch break,
we wanted to show you
around the campus,
if you don't mind.
[gasps]
Here it comes.
[HOKUTO] For you. It's
konpeito candy and you can
have some if you come with us.
What?
I hate standing here
and not being able
to say anything!
Can't we at least tell
her that he does this
" konpeito candy" thing
to people all of the time?
Don't you dare, Ukki!
If you do, I'm not
gonna get my ten yen!
[HOKUTO] What are you two
squirming about over there?
It's not good for you
to hold it if you need
to go to the bathroom, 'least
that's what my grandma says.
The grandma bit again!
I have to say something!
It's ten yen, Ukki!
Please, let me have this!
Consider my soul!
[HOKUTO] Thank you for
agreeing to come with us.
The cafeteria is called
the "Garden Terrace."
That's weird.
Usually this place is so packed
that they sell out
of meal tickets.
Hm? Hey, isn't that...?
I meant what I said.
Seek me out if you have
any trouble at all.
[MAKOTO chuckles] I'm available,
too, if you need me.
I'm on the broadcast committee,
so I'm good at
finding information.
That tends to come in handy.
You can always talk to me, too!
And I know this is kinda sudden,
but can I please
borrow some money?
--[giggles] Pretty please?
--[ANZU] Uh...
If you haven't figured it out
yet, this guy's an idiot.
I wouldn't advise getting
involved with him.
Hokke, what are
you saying? Stop!
Now for the rest of our
lives, she's gonna think
I'm a moron because of you!
[whines]
We're getting off topic here.
I'll start again
from the beginning.
This is Yumenosaki
Private Academy.
A school that grooms
future idols.
[MAKOTO]
There is also a standard course
for more traditional students.
[HOKUTO]
Not everyone who studies here
is currently working.
There are those who have
already made their debut,
but don't have continuous
jobs as idols.
You're part of
that group, right?
Yeah, but that's kind
of a sore spot for me.
I'd be so grateful if you
wouldn't talk about it.
Uh-- Of course.
I'm sorry. Anyway.
At this school, all the
resources that are needed
to improve your skills
and talents as an idol
are part of the curriculum.
As students in the idol course,
we spend our days
training intensely.
This school was created
for idols, by idols.
We work extremely hard
becoming better idols
than we were the day before.
[ANZU]
Hm.
[guitar strums]
Sounds like a guitar.
Wait, does that mean...?
[SUBARU]
Totally!
That's why no one's
here right now!
I knew something was weird!
I see.
Then, this might be
a good opportunity.
All right, transfer student,
now's your chance
to witness what this
school is really like.
Hold on, what does that mean?
Seeing is believing, isn't it?
Let's go.
We'll show you Yumenosaki
Academy's famous DreFes.
'Sup, yo!
Competition belongs
in a man's world!
Backstage, the blood's boiling.
And our competitors are
ready to throw down!
Ready to watch two guys
in a battle of wills?
[TETORA]
I forgot to introduce myself!
I'm Nagumo Tetora,
host for the DreFes
Ryuu-ou-sen match!
I'm also a first year
in the Karate Club!
Yeah, boi! I love
weight training!
I love eating kalbi .
And my dream for
the future is
to become the manliest
man of all time!
[STUDENT 01A]
No one asked you!
[SUBARU]
Ah!
You gotta be kidding.
It feels like this DreFes
is turning into a riot.
What's "DreFes" mean?
I can explain that.
As part of the Yumenosaki
Academy idol course,
we regularly have sudden,
pop up events
called "Dream Idol Festivals,"
or "DreFes" for short.
You can think of it as
a competition to see
who has superior idol skills.
These work like tests
at traditional schools.
If you win, your rank
goes up, you get rewards,
and the school
treats you better.
It teaches us how
to handle competitions
and inspires students
to work harder.
That's its original purpose.
In the DreFes, we're
ranked from SS to B1.
This is the lowest level, B1.
For various reasons,
events that are ranked A1
and higher have become
DreFes in name only,
so you'll find that these shows
are the most free and lively.
"Various reasons"?
Look. This is the B1
Ryuu-ou-sen title match.
Ryuu-ou-sen!
--[yelps]
--[MAKOTO] Uh, why did you
say it like the name
of an ultimate move?
Anyway, the purpose
of this DreFes
is to find the strongest
person in the school.
The contestant you've
all been waiting for
has finally arrived!
It's the challenger!
At 5'7" and weighing
in at a 128 pounds,
he's called the "Snapping
Demon of the Band Club!"
Mad dog, Ogami Koga!
I'm ready to sink my claws
into the souls of fools!
I'll bite your flesh
and tear it apart
before drinking
your fresh blood!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Enjoy the rapture of this moment
before you become
my next victim!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Wow! He's so cool!
Gami- san ! Gami- san !
For real?
Don't you dare pretend
like we're friends
and call me by
a nickname, Akehoshi!
You know I'm a lone wolf
and don't rely on anyone!
When I stand at the top,
I'll stand alone!
I don't need
divine intervention.
I'm the reason I'm
standing on this stage!
[laughs] Yay!
[TETORA]
This is bad, you guys!
Did you happen to see
our chief anywhere?
Huh?
By "chief," do you
mean the captain
of the Karate Club?
Yeah, that's right.
He was supposed to go
up against Ogami,
but when I looked backstage,
he wasn't there yet!
Oh!
I saw him in the cafeteria
earlier eating spaghetti!
[TETORA]
That's ridiculous!
At this point, he's going
to have to lose by default!
[groans] What the heck,
chief! Where are you?
[KURO] What are you
screaming about, Tetsu?
[laughs] Chief! You made it!
You scared the crap out of me!
Hey, Tetsu. You happen to
have a handkerchief on ya?
Uh... A handkerchief?
Lemme see here.
[ANZU]
Have mine.
[MAKOTO]
Wait, what are you doing?
She's about to save the day!
Who are you? And why
haven't I seen you around?
[ANZU gasps]
Guess it doesn't matter.
Thanks for the save, love.
I'll get it back to you clean.
[KOGA]
What do we have here?
So, the champ
decided to show up?
Finally, I was gettin' bored.
[KOGA cackles]
I could use a little
entertainment right now,
and I'm counting on you!
You're the strongest man
in Yumenosaki Academy.
You can handle it.
He's the captain of
the Karate Club here.
Kiryu Kuro, third year student.
Is that a lone pup
I hear yappin'?
Didn't your master train you
to respect your upperclassmen?
[KOGA]
Heh.
If you wanna beat me,
you'll have to bring out Sakuma!
But I guess that's
not really an option.
What a shame.
At least you can help me
work off my lunch.
Hah!
It's an honor to reintroduce
you to our champion!
He's 5'10", weighs 143 pounds,
and he's the strongest man
in Yumenosaki Academy.
Kiryu Kuro!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[laughs] I've been
waiting for you!
It wouldn't have been any fun
just to win this
thing by default.
Bring it on! Come punch me!
Lemme see what ya got.
I'll snap your fingers
clean off your hands.
Huh?
[KURO grunts]
[KURO]
He dodged me.
Guess he's not all
talk after all.
Brat!
[gasps]
[KOGA]
What's with this bastard?
I'm not feeling any
bloodlust from him at all!
He acts like he's
going for a walk,
and then turns
around with a kick.
Step it up!
I know you're
holding back on me!
Time to stop playing around!
Sorry, can't do that.
I was really hoping to get
this over with quickly.
Guess I was too optimistic.
Jeez, what kind of
crazy matchup is this?
A physical one!
Fighting's allowed
in the Ryuu-ou-sen!
As part of the competition,
you can punch and kick
the person you're
performing against.
Is that what they meant by
"finding the strongest
person in the school"?
Complete anarchy.
Sounds like a B1.
[laughs] Amazing! It's like
watching professional
martial arts right
here at school!
[KURO] If you like that guitar,
I suggest you tighten your grip!
[TETORA]
Whoa! Look at that!
Ogami has been blown
clear out of the ring!
[KOGA grunts]
[yells]
Uh-- [grunts]
[SUBARU, HOKUTO]
Transfer student!
[MAKOTO
Transfer student?
[groaning]
[STUDENT 01D]
That's so mean, Koga!
[STUDENT 01E]
Wait, is that a girl?
[STUDENT 01F]
From the production course?
Shut up! I may've left the ring,
but I haven't touched
the ground yet.
[TETORA grunts]
The fight's just beginning!
Uh...
Are you all right?
Speak to us.
I'm okay.
Hey. Idiot!
The match has been decided.
No matter how you look
at it, you've lost!
Say what?
Who died and put you
in charge, ya bookworm?
[STUDENT 01G]
Stop messing around!
[STUDENT 01H]
You've already lost!
[giggles] He's squealing
like a little piggy.
No, more like a puppy with
his tail between his legs.
[KEITO chuckles]
If you've got a problem with
me, then come 'n get some!
[HOKUTO]
Don't misjudge your opponent.
You fool!
Remember what's important.
Who our real enemy is.
[gasps]
[footsteps]
[KEITO]
Quiet, everyone!
We're executives from
the student council!
[ALL gasp]
The school did not give you
permission for this DreFes.
According to Article 4
of the Yumenosaki...
[STUDENT 01I]
The student council?
[STUDENT 01J]
Why? They should be busy
with paperwork during lunch.
Take a look around.
You're completely surrounded.
I knew you'd all try
something if I spread
the rumor we were busy,
and you didn't disappoint me.
How terribly expected.
Now you'll get what's coming
to you, troublemakers.
Listen up! I am vice
president, Hasumi Keito.
I represent the student
council president.
In the name of Tenshouin Eichi,
I shall etch the school rules
onto your puny brains!
Shoot! This is so not good!
Well, now.
Looks like our fight's paused.
Until the next time. Punk.
Huh? Tch. Damn it.
[laughing] You're making too
much of a fuss, piggies!
There's no use in
trying to escape. Kay?
Now be good and run back
into the livestock shed.
This is oppression, Vice Prez.
The Ryuu-ou-sen is a DreFes
with a long tradition.
It's something that the
Karate Club upperclassmen
passed down to us,
and we are proud of it!
We must retain order here.
Until the president returns,
I will be the backbone
of peace at this school.
The champion of its law.
Kiryu.
You will also receive punishment
for your actions today.
Even if we are both
in the same unit.
[KURO]
Hmph.
[SUBARU yells]
Hang in there, transfer student!
Please come back to
the world of the living!
[BOYS gasp]
Shh.
[ALL laugh]
[bell rings]
[MAKOTO]
Thanks.
Without you, we
wouldn't've been able
to sneak past the
student council.
It's like you're our very
own magician, Sally.
It wasn't magic, just good luck.
Anyway, it's not
always like that.
I just happen to
be pretty clever
when I'm around you guys.
Because we're all in this
together. Makes sense!
By the way, how's
that girl doing?
[door clicks]
Mr. Sagami!
[MAKOTO]
How's the transfer student?
Ah, don't be concerned.
I don't think she was injured.
She's just getting
some rest right now.
Transfer student?
Yeah, she's the first student
in the production course
that started here on
a provisional basis.
It's always just been
boys in the idol track,
so she'll be the
only female student
at the academy for a while.
Oh. A future producer, huh?
That's right. This
could be a good thing.
Yumenosaki Academy has
gotten stiff because of its
longstanding traditions
and rules.
Maybe she can bring
a little excitement.
Hey, Sagami. Where's Hokke?
[SAGAMI] He's with the
transfer student inside.
[MAKOTO] Jeez, did he forget
he has friends out here?
He doesn't have to watch
over her all by himself.
Yeah, right?
We're supposed to share any
hardships with each other.
We can build ourselves up.
One-by-one, together.
Eventually, we'll grow so big,
we can reach the heavens.
And our fingertips
will brush the stars.
Mm... Actually, we'll be the
sparkling wonders ourselves.
We'll become stars.
[HOKUTO] She looks so fragile
just lying there like that.
I feel bad. Your
first day was ruined.
But that's not all.
There's one more thing
that I need to apologize
to you about.
I'm afraid that lied
to you earlier today.
This academy isn't
really a school
made for idols,
by idols, like I said.
More precisely, this is a school
for the chosen, elite idols.
Outcasts like us who aren't
singled out as being superior
will never see spotlights
from the stage.
It's true that this school
does continue to turn out
a large number of celebrities.
But they're trained like
livestock in this place,
with no sense of human kindness.
The student council is
what rules over the academy
and keeps that system in
place. They're unbending.
That's why...
...somehow, we must bring
about a revolution.
In order to tear down
the student council
and reform this school,
we'll fight to the end,
risking our lives.
And you might turn out to
be the one to lead the way.
I have a hunch
that'll be the case.
No. I want it to be true.
That's why we pray
that your heart
will resonate with ours,
transfer student.
So, you see,
you're the shining hope
we've been wishing for.
The one who will help
us change this school.
[BOYS gasp, laugh]
[ANZU]
It was on that day,
the revolution they'd
longed for quietly began.