[CHILDREN chattering]
Can you guess what I am?
[CHIAKI] I've got some
amazing news for you guys.
I've been working
on something great.
It's gonna be so
good for RYUSEITAI.
We're gonna create our own
version of this park hero show,
where even more kids will
be able to watch us perform
on a huge stage at a theme
park. It'll be awesome!
A hero show combined
with a concert.
We'll call it "Supernova"!
[ANZU]
After Trickstar won the DDD,
and successfully
sparked a revolution,
the school's atmosphere finally
started to change
little by little.
[door opens]
[CHIAKI]
Tenshouin!
You gonna say anything
about my project proposal?
Whaddya think?
Right, then.
I'm sorry, I rejected it.
[gasps] What? Why?
Chiaki, I need you to calm
down for just a moment
and think about
your position here.
I'm an ally of justice
here to protect the school!
I am Morisawa Chiaki.
My heart is Ryusei Red just like
the burning, bright red sun!
Yes, it's cute.
I get that RYUSEITAI's
concept is inspired by heroes,
but you're still just
idols--not actual heroes.
I know, but so what?
So, sorry if I'm not being
completely clear here.
Your request goes against
student council policy.
I can't fund an official DreFes
so you can pretend
you're heroes.
You've got it wrong!
It's not like that.
We just wanna do
a concert in the theme park!
But RYUSEITAI's working
with a tight budget.
[EICHI] I understand,
but as you can see,
other units have also
submitted new proposals.
I can't exactly show
favoritism to one group.
[CHIAKI grunts]
[door closes]
Oh, hey, Anzu!
How's it going?
I can't believe I forgot!
You're in the production
course, right?
That's right.
[VILLAIN 13A laughs]
[TETORA]
No way!
So what does that mean?
He rejected the whole thing?
That's the way
I understood it, yeah.
Wow!
Guess I was right!
Can I go home now?
No, hold on a sec.
It doesn't mean he
intends to give up
on the proposal completely.
He wants to make it work
and told me to continue
prepping for it.
How's he plan to do that?
It was shut down.
I honestly have no clue.
He's relentless.
He's even making us watch
a bunch of tokusatsu
videos to prep.
[MIDORI] I'm so confused as
to what an idol is anymore.
And what does all this hero
stuff have to do with it?
'Cause our next
performance is s'posed
to be a hero show
if things go right.
[SHINOBU]
Complete with special effects.
He said we would even
have some fighting scenes.
Speaking of which, I just
realized Shinkai's not here.
Kinda not into it being just
us first-years in charge.
Sounds like a lot of pressure.
Guess we don't have a choice.
This sucks.
[KURO gasps]
Red Ogre, how are you doing?
Scared the crap out of me.
Don't jump out
at people like that.
Anyway, sounds like
RYUSEITAI is in a bind.
Sure you have time
to be swimming in there?
I heard you're a hero now,
so shouldn't you be out
rescuing your
friends or something?
I don't know what
I should or shouldn't do.
It was never my
goal to be a hero,
and I'm not sure I'm a fan.
Still, you should get
out of the fountain.
Your husband is out
running errands, right?
So go be a good wife
and get home to your family.
That's funny.
Chiaki isn't my spouse,
we're just very close.
And those kids must think
I'm some "strange organism"
floating around.
They have no idea who
I am or what I represent.
[KURO] Heh! Yeah,
you're probably right.
[KANATA] Regardless,
I guess I should help out more.
It's my job, after all--
protecting RYUSEITAI, and
Chiaki's dream, of course.
Oh, hey, is that
Chiichan's proposal?
Are you helping him edit it?
I am, but that doesn't
mean it'll get approved--
the criteria's very strict.
The fact that he accepted
the submission at all
is a bigger achievement
than Chiaki could've made
on his own, believe me.
Looks like we got another
interview request.
Our schedule's
already overwhelming.
Guess it's a good
problem to have.
The struggles
of winning the DDD.
Sorry you're so overwhelmed.
I wish I could be
a better help to you.
No worries, seriously.
We'll be fine.
We shouldn't lean on you
this much in the first place.
But that's why everyone wants
you to be their producer.
[SUBARU]
Let's give it all we've got!
Yeah!
[KANATA]
Okay.
Now, one, and two,
three, and that's four.
Then we go back
to two, three, four!
[MIDORI, TETORA, SHINOBU]
Whoa.
[TETORA] Shinkai's
amazing... and so graceful!
[SHINOBU] He lives up to being
one of the Three Eccentrics.
[MIDORI] I thought
he was just a weird guy,
but maybe there's
more to him than that?
[door opens]
Good work, everyone!
Is that Lady Anzu next to you?
What is she doing here?
Well, I asked her to help me
rewrite my proposal and she did.
The one I wrote
originally was crap,
but this one really
gets the point across.
Oh, man, are you
sure about this?
"A bunch of bad guys invade,
and the heroes immediately
come to beat them up"?
[MIDORI] I don't know if you
can really call that a proposal.
But the little space
monster drawings
on the side are
endearing, I guess.
They're masterpieces!
I also designed a giant robot!
[BOTH gasp]
Do you expect us to build
that thing for a performance?
Now you know why I asked
her to help me rewrite it.
Writing good proposals is
a skill producers need to hone,
so it's a win-win.
She just needs to phrase it in a
way that makes it sound amazing.
If we get the funds, we won't
have to build it ourselves.
And Tenshouin gets
more open-minded
with each submission.
It's much easier to picture.
Okay, Kanata, I have
a favor to ask of you.
Since I'm trying to incorporate
an extra performance
in this production,
I'm wondering if you could
lead the underclassmen.
Well...
...at first glance, it's looking
pretty impossible for the kids.
I can see that.
How can we tweak it so it
would work with just me and you?
Hold it, Commander.
Don't you think it's unfair
for you to underestimate us?
We're members of
RYUSEITAI, too, ya know?
Did I just hear you recognize
yourself as a part of RYUSEITAI?
Thank you, Nagumo! Thank you!
[TETORA]
Stop! What're you doing?
Oh! I wasn't trying
to underestimate you.
On the contrary, I'm
currently making adjustments
to help you shine
at your brightest.
We should probably head to
the meeting at the theme park.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to make sure I'm in top shape!
If I were you, I'd do the same!
See ya later!
What was that all about?
Man, I really thought
he'd be bummed
when the proposal was
rejected the first time.
Oh, he is. He's just
very good at faking it.
You know him--
forever wanting
to be the cool guy.
Hey, Nagumo, what's the deal?
You're into this idea now?
You used to say pretend
hero stuff was dumb.
But all of a sudden,
you're willing to participate?
Well, that part hasn't changed.
I still think
it's pretty stupid,
but I don't really
have a choice.
I didn't get into the
Chief's team, AKATSUKI,
so I'm making the best of this.
I originally joined RYUSEITAI
'cause it was all that was left.
I didn't want to, and
tokusatsu was so immature.
But after giving
it some thought,
I realized being a hero
could lead me to my dream
of becoming the
manliest man among men.
So now, I'm gonna
give it my best shot!
And I'll stay
if it's working out!
You don't need to make
up your mind right now.
Take your time.
You are all still children.
Enjoy learning from
your experiences
and don't be in such
a rush to grow up.
Not to say it
isn't bothersome
for us to care for you
until you're grown,
but at least we can try to
protect you along your journey.
Floating, floating.
[ANZU] And just
like that, there it was.
The big day had finally arrived.
Right!
[MIDORI]
I'll see ya later.
[CITIZEN 13A]
What do you wanna do first?
[CITIZEN 13B]
How about a rollercoaster?
Heck, yeah! Let's do it!
I wanna do the fastest one
first in case it gets crowded.
[CITIZEN 13A]
Yeah, good call!
[SHINOBU grunts]
--Hey.
--[yelps]
Uh, hey! What's up, Lady Anzu?
I didn't expect you
to be here so early.
Oh, right.
Well, I'm not very familiar
with the layout of this theater.
I wanted to be early so I could
walk around and get comfortable.
So here's the thing!
I don't wanna ruin this.
I'm the type of ninja
who gets extremely stressed
and sick when
I'm in a new place.
Are you feeling okay?
Don't! I understand
you mean well,
but if you push my hair whorl,
it's gonna stunt my growth!
Leave me alone!
I'm so sorry!
Whoa. Wait...
Never mind.
I actually feel much calmer now.
Thank you for talking
to me, Lady Anzu.
I care, you know?
I just want to make sure
the show's a success.
I'm so grateful.
RYUSEITAI is the only unit that
would accept someone like me.
And because of that,
I want these guys to be
in my life for a long time.
That's great.
What's that? Wow.
[CHILDREN laughing]
[CHILD 13A]
Bye, orange bear!
[CHILD 13B]
See ya!
--[SHINOBU] Midori...
--[MIDORI screams]
[SHINOBU]
...what are you doing?
You scared me.
I got here early, so I figured
I'd pass out flyers and stuff.
I appreciate how
hard you're working.
Do you need any help?
No, thank you.
I'm okay. I'd rather be alone.
All right, but please
keep in mind that
if there's something upsetting
you, you can always talk to me.
Okay, thanks.
But somehow I feel
so much better
just knowing that you care.
I'm fine guys, I promise.
[squeaking]
[SHINOBU sighs]
[CROWD chattering]
It's almost time.
[CHILD 13C]
Is it gonna start now?
This is good!
They call it a "shake."
It's like ice cream you can
drink. That's a first for me!
It brings me great joy to know
you're experiencing
the theme park to its fullest.
But that's not to say I've
forgotten about work, of course.
Don't you worry now.
I'm looking forward to
auditing RYUSEITAI's Supernova.
[ANZU, TRICKSTAR
MEMBERS giggling]
Oh, hi, president.
[HOKUTO]
Didn't expect to see you here.
Are you by yourself?
Where's Himemiya today?
He's off training
with Master Hibiki.
The young master has chosen
to deal with our DDD loss
in his own way, per usual.
I've no doubt he'll grow
from this experience.
Agreed.
'Scuse me. You
approved our proposal?
Thank you so much.
It reached a level that
I could sign off on.
Good job in getting it there.
This stage is
ideal for showcasing
RYUSEITAI's current ability.
According to legend,
RYUSEITAI was most likely
Yumenosaki Academy's
first ever idol unit.
[EICHI]
Chiaki was a big part of that.
Even during tumultuous times,
he continued to be
an active member.
Chiaki may be impulsive
and make reckless decisions,
but he's no idiot.
I want the best for him
with all my heart.
So, uh, how're the costumes?
Are you having any issues?
Nope. You did an amazing job.
The fit and the construction
are perfect. Thank you.
I can't wait to see
'em from the audience.
Good luck.
[buzzer sounds]
[footsteps]
[CHIAKI] Welcome to RYUSEITAI's
performance featuring
Yumenosaki Academy's
super rangers!
Who's ready to create
this Supernova?
[KANATA] Good afternoon!
I'm so happy to see all of you!
I only see Masters
Shinkai and Morisawa.
Where're the first-year members?
In the original proposal,
it was just a typical hero show.
Defeat some bad guys
and monsters
followed by a happy ending.
Seen it all before.
However, I needed it to
feel more like a concert
with experienced performers,
so they took some
time to rewrite it.
And "Supernova" came
from that compromise.
[MIDORI]
Ahh!
[TETORA]
Roar!
[MIDORI, TETORA grunt]
[EICHI] So, for the first half
of the show, we'll only see
third-years singing and
dancing to create the vibe.
That's not to say that
the first-year students
aren't still going to perform.
I get it now. They're
in those monster costumes.
[SHINOBU]
Nin!
[CHIAKI, KANATA grunt]
[CROWD gasping]
Everything's going as planned.
Looks like it's working!
And the best part is
the kiddos are happy!
That's the best reward any of
us could ever hope to receive.
I've gotta show Tenshouin
my gratitude somehow.
Dear predecessors,
I hope you're watching.
After many years, your legacy
is still alive and strong.
This is RYUSEITAI now.
We fight to protect justice!
[ALL grunting]
--[CHIAKI grunts]
--[MONSTERS groan]
I will boldly fight any evil
that dares to stand between
me and what is right!
We owe it to our children
and underclassmen.
They deserve a world
that is safe and just.
It's up to us!
Are those tears?
I hope you're crying out of joy.
After all...
...your dreams
are coming true!
You've worked hard.
You deserve it!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHIAKI grunts]
Whoa, is everything
okay? Are you?
Oh, yeah! This next
part's a little tricky
but nothing you
and I can't handle...
...I think. You in?
It's rude to assume.
Do you have any idea who
you're talking to right now?
You know I'm kidding, of course.
I'm in. I'll stand
beside you through it all.
That's a promise and a vow.
The ocean can
be quiet and gentle,
while walking on land
can be rough and stifling
for somebody like me.
[CROWD shouts]
But I'm certain that
this is where I belong.
And I'll never forget
that you're the one
who brought me here.
Thanks.
[MONSTERS]
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Never fear!
I am here for you!
Ryusei Chop!
What has happened?
I fear that last attack used up
all of the fighting
strength I had left!
I feel myself getting weak!
I have no strength
left to stand!
Down goes Blue!
[KIDS gasp]
[CHIAKI]
Blue! Come back!
We still have
enemies left to fight!
But I feel I may be
at my limit as well.
Is this the end? It can't be!
Justice... RYUSEITAI
will prevail!
Won't it, kids?
Cheer if you believe!
--[SUBARU, MAKOTO] Come on!
--[HOKUTO] RYUSEITAI!
[CHILD 13D]
You can do it!
[CROWD cheering]
This is the power...
of justice! [grunts]
[ALL groan]
I understand now. So the
monster first-year students
transform into allies of
justice as a starting point.
And then, in time, they become
the new members
of RYUSEITAI, right?
Right.
I saw the value of the story
right away and approved it.
[CROWD cheering]
[MIDORI sighs]
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Every time I look at you,
it seems like something's up.
Maybe.
I'll tell you later if
we have time. Thank you.
Don't you dare shut us out.
If there's something wrong,
you need to tell us what it is!
We're all in this!
I'm also doing my best to
become a member of RYUSEITAI!
There's nothing
you're going through
that we can't understand!
Thanks, Nagumo.
It's okay to lean on
your friends for help.
[MIDORI] Everyone's so
positive. I envy them.
The only reason I'm here is
because I went with the flow.
I saw an old classmate from
middle school this morning.
He looked so happy.
Seeing him live his life
like a normal high school
kid really got to me.
I know that if I'd
taken a different path
without so many
high expectations,
I could've been happy, too.
--[KANATA] Midori?
--[gasps]
I'm sorry, I zoned out!
It's all right, I promise.
Take some deep
breaths and relax.
Come on, deep breath in.
[MIDORI inhales]
Here they are, but
they need more energy!
So can we cheer again
for our first-year members?
[CROWD cheers]
[CHIAKI]
It's working!
They heard your cheers
and are here to save us!
[CROWD shouting]
An alien?
Does that mean they're back?
What do ya say?
Can you give us a hand?
--[SHINOBU, MIDORI] Yeah!
--[TETORA] All right!
[MIDORI]
It was my choice.
I wasn't interested in
conventional happiness.
[CHIAKI]
Green!
[MIDORI grunts]
[CROWD cheering]
[MIDORI] But even so, I think
I might be just as happy
if not happier than he is.
[CITIZEN 13A]
You can do it! I believe in you!
[MIDORI]
I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
[CHIAKI] All right, let's go!
Job well done, Meteors!
Now it's time to return this
shining justice to the world!
[RYUSEITAI MEMBERS]
All right!
Red flames serve
as proof of justice!
That's why the sun
of life burns so bright!
I'm Ryusei Red! Morisawa Chiaki!
Blue flames represent the
proof of magic and mystery
created from the heart
of the deep blue sea!
I'm Ryusei Blue!
Shinkai Kanata! Sparkle!
Yellow flames
represent proof of hope!
A ray of miracles
shines in the dark!
I'm Ryusei Yellow!
Sengoku Shinobu!
Black flames are
the proof of hard work!
With a burning, fighting
spirit covered in mud,
I'm Ryusei Black! Nagumo Tetora!
Green flames are the
proof of true affection!
It's also proof
of healing and stuff.
I'm Ryusei Green!
Takamine Midori!
You will get to
know us! Our name...
[ALL]
...is RYUSEITAI!
We're excited to
bring you Supernova!
We're working on real superhero
time and that begins now!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD cheering]
All right, kids,
do you like heroes?
[KIDS]
We love heroes a whole bunch!
I love heroes, too.
Idols can be heroes
if they stay strong
and do the right thing!
They're all on your
side no matter what!
They protect the
peace in your lives!
We promise to bring you music
yesterday, today, tomorrow,
and everyday after that!
We're here with you,
even if we're on stage
singing to you out there.
We promise to shine
surely, strongly, and justly!
[RYUSEITAI MEMBERS]
Thank you all very much!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANZU]
Good work, you guys!
Right back atcha! Thank you!
Yes, thank you, Anzu.
It's because of you that
Supernova was such a huge hit!
I loved seeing how
happy it made the kids.
Oh, yeah, you never said.
Do you like heroes, Kanata?
[KANATA]
Hm?
I was just wondering,
if I hadn't dragged you
into helping with
RYUSEITAI, would you--
I mean, would any of you have
ever entertained the thought
of becoming heroes, or that
you might already be one?
They wouldn't have stayed
around if they disliked it.
They'd drift off like seafoam.
Me, too, but I'm here.
I don't know what
heroes have to do
or even what it
takes to become one,
but I'm fairly certain I could
come to love this
special unit very much.
And that includes
you, of course.
I'm loving you all
more and more each day!
Really? I feel the same way!
Hey, you see that shooting star?
What should I wish for? Right!
I wish for a cute girlfriend
to make my lunches!
[KANATA laughs]
[KANATA]
This is when most people
would've wished for
world peace, hero!