[ANZU] The leaves are beginning
to change all around us.
It feels like
autumn is setting in.
Fueled by their loss
at the Summer Live,
Trickstar is on
a nationwide pilgrimage
to hone their skills for
a comeback performance.
[ANZU]
Mm.
[EICHI]
Have you seen it yet?
The proposal for
Trickstar's Revenge Match.
I was under the impression
that you requested a competition
with Reimei Academy's Eve.
[EICHI]
I did, but
we received a rather strange
offer from Cosmic Production.
That's the name of Eve's agency.
Oh, wow.
[TORI]
Shuetsu Academy?
Which is known as an affiliate
school of Reimei Academy.
They replied inviting
Trickstar to participate
in their Autumn Live.
[YUZURU]
Does that mean their opponents
would then be Adam
instead of Eve?
Right.
That is a strange offer.
[TORI]
Hm?
Trickstar doesn't
think it's that odd.
They're jumping
at the opportunity
and planning to accept.
I'm a little worried.
You-know-who goes
to Shuetsu Academy.
What?! Who does?!
What are you talking about?!
Please calm down. I'll tell you
the whole story in due time.
On a different note,
I also have a proposal,
dear President.
[MAO panting]
Sorry I'm late, guys!
You okay, Sally?
Ritsu refused to wake up
this morning, as usual,
then I had to make him breakfast
and get him dressed, too.
He can be such a pain!
I'm surprised you
made it here at all!
All right, let's go!
To Shuitsu--
Uh, uh, I mean,
to Shuetsu Academy!
--[MAKOTO] Aw, yeah!
--[GROUP] Yeah!
[SUBARU] Can you believe
we'll be staying there
for a whole week?
I'm amazed that they
bothered to arrange hotels
for every one of us, y'know?
It feels like a school trip!
I can't wait to play games and
have pillow fights every night!
You do realize we're going
out there for work, right?
Adam will also be
there. Get ready.
Yes, but that doesn't matter.
My proposal was
a rematch with Eve.
Apparently, there was
some political interference.
But Adam is on par with Eve, so
that's who we're battling now.
Talk about short notice.
Look closely at
the edited proposal.
It doesn't say if it's
a real rematch or not.
What do you mean?
Shuetsu Academy's
affiliate school idols
always attend the Autumn Live.
So we could be featured
as the guest performers.
Well, if that's the case,
then it's not actually a fair
rematch of the Summer Live.
This all feels like someone
is enjoying watching us
dance in the palm of their hand.
But we're already
on our way there,
so we may as well
try to have fun, right?
I can't wait to see what
the members of Adam are like!
I'm so excited!
Slow down. Let's focus on
the concert ahead first.
[SUBARU]
Is this the place?
Wow, their campus
is freakishly quiet.
[TSUMUGI]
Hey!
[TRICKSTAR MEMBERS gasp]
[TSUMUGI]
Trickstar! You made it!
I've been waiting for you.
Is that really you, Ao, sir?
What are you
doing at this school?
Nobody told you, I guess?
I've been sent here
to support you guys.
A few others from Yumenosaki
will be there to
cheer you on, as well.
He... I mean, Nagisa used
to go to school there, too.
We were in the old
fine unit together.
Anyway, we're friends,
so I figured I'd make myself
available to help if needed.
[GROUP]
Thank you very much!
[SUBARU]
This place is gigantic!
Look at the pretty, shiny floor!
The members of Adam all have
their own reception offices?
Shuetsu Academy must be
a highly ranked school.
Yeah, I think I know why.
I heard that they only
accept honor students
from all the affiliate schools.
And since honor
students can have
multiple reception offices
and practice rooms, they do.
Must be nice to
be a student here.
Yeah, unless you're
not an honor student.
Then you'd be stuck
maintaining the facility
and other exciting chores.
Even though they're students?
Sazanami said they're
not considered equal.
He said that non-honor
students of Shuetsu
are basically
treated like slaves.
[TSUMUGI]
Looks like this is it.
Weird. It's locked.
[STUDENT A] That area's off
limits to non-honor students.
Unless you have
an assigned tablet.
I'm very sorry, but all
visitors will need to leave.
[phone rings]
[ALL gasping]
Yes, I understand, sir!
Please accept my apologies.
I've just been informed
that Master Saegusa
is at the school gate.
Please, allow me
to guide you there.
Salute!
Welcome to Shuetsu Academy.
I am delighted
that you've arrived.
I'm Saegusa Ibara
from the unit Adam.
I am pleased to meet you.
I trust this will be
a positive experience.
I look forward to
working with you.
Yeah! Me, too!
What a treat this is.
To have such a talented
unit participating with us.
We are quite fortunate indeed.
I have to say,
I am a huge fan of yours!
[HOKUTO] He's much more
aggressive than I expected.
Nice to meet you, Saegusa.
Is Nagisa around somewhere?
Oh, His Excellency was
finishing up an excavation
and got carried away.
He's not quite fit to
be seen at the moment.
But I'll have him introduce
himself a little later,
after he's freshened up a bit.
His who?
Oh. Ran Nagisa, of course.
See, I used to be in
a military-like place.
Military?
[IBARA] Never mind that! Just
know that you're most welcome!
I have a feeling we're all going
to liven things up around here!
[IBARA laughs]
[SUBARU] There's even
practice clothes for us?
You guys are on top of it!
Well, beautiful boys
look good in everything.
[chuckles] Beautiful? Come on!
Where's your outfit, Barry?
We should practice
a song together!
Best way to get to know our
skills is to work with them!
When you said Barry,
you meant me, right?
Which must mean that
you're quite skilled
at informal communication.
I'm learning so much.
It's just a nickname.
Look, we're doing a
performance together,
so shouldn't we be friends?
[MAKOTO]
Akehoshi!
Please stop running
off without us!
You shouldn't be alone in
enemy territory. It's not safe.
Sorry, sorry.
Enemy territory? You're more
competitive than I thought.
The only agenda we have
is to get along with you.
Is that so? How strange.
With a name like Adam,
I just assumed you would
be aggressive and intense.
--Hey.
--[MAKOTO gasps]
Where'd they go?
Your producer and the other
one went to turn in your forms.
In the meantime,
I'd be happy to give you
all a tour of the facility.
[SUBARU]
What's this?
[IBARA] A tablet we
distribute to all the students
in our agency. You can be
temporary CosPro members.
It will only stay
activated until you leave.
CosPro?
It's short for
Cosmic Production,
the name of our agency.
Students from Shuetsu and
Reimei Academy all belong to it.
They rep affiliate students,
too, but it's mostly exclusive.
There are many benefits.
You'll receive training
and management as well.
They'll probably represent
you as affiliate honor students
for the duration
of the Autumn Live.
It just makes filling
out paperwork simpler.
Please start the
app on your tablet.
This one?
[SUBARU]
Wow! Look at that!
You'll find there are many
facilities on the campus
you cannot access
without this app.
[MAKOTO]
This is amazing!
[HOKUTO] It's much better
equipped than I imagined.
Feels like that paperwork
took forever to fill out.
Yeah.
[clink]
Huh? What was that?
You hear it?
Uh, great, so this
place is haunted.
[clinking]
Let's check the map.
Here we go.
Looks like this is
Adam's reception office.
[door opening]
[MAO]
Uh, hello?
[BOTH gasp]
Hello there.
What is it?
Sorry, we just
heard a strange noise
and didn't know anyone was here!
[NAGISA] You're from
Trickstar, aren't you?
And you are?
I'm a producer!
Pardon us, sir! My name's
Isara Mao from Trickstar!
It's nice to meet you!
Likewise.
I know you. You're the
leader of Eden and Adam.
You're Ran Nagisa, right?
You used to be in fine.
And you're from--
[NAGISA]
Titles are so exhausting,
don't you think?
Please call me Nagisa.
I don't want to be bound by
labels or names. Just free.
[MAO]
What's going on?
He made me change
clothes and start dancing.
[ANZU]
That's strange.
He isn't even paying
attention to Isara.
[MAO grunts]
Okay. I've got a question
I'd like to ask you now.
[NAGISA]
All right.
I wanna know what
that rock thing is.
I've no clue.
And that is why it intrigues me.
It's something I excavated
from an ancient layer of earth.
How riveting. Still,
I'd rather you look at me.
[NAGISA]
Would you?
I realize, from your
worldly perspective,
that thing is more important.
But by not looking,
you're assuming I'm harmless.
Know what I mean?
I was just kidding!
It felt right at the time!
[NAGISA]
It's all right.
Though, I admit,
what you say saddens me.
Why?
[NAGISA] It reminds me so much
of something Eichi would say.
None can doubt you are
a Yumenosaki Academy student.
No desire to improve,
but you'll fight each other
and struggle to find
an optimal solution.
You repeat this several times
hoping it'll make
you a better person.
It's the innate desire
of all living creatures.
But it makes me sad
because stagnation equals death.
And if killing each other is
the duty of living creatures,
well then, I want
deliverance from that.
What I desire most is a
world free from conflict.
When I look at the living,
what I see are
God's failed creations.
To live is torture.
Life is divine punishment.
Life is the original sin
that cannot be forgiven.
Is it wrong to long to be free?
Do you blame me for wanting
to be released from that trap?
Heh. You will
not get in my way.
If you try to keep me imprisoned
here, you will certainly fail
and I will take you down
with me instead.
All of you.
[SUBARU]
That was so good!
I'm stuffed!
The cafeteria here is amazing!
They provide optimum meals
made by a personal chef,
and everyone has
their own nutritionist!
[HOKUTO]
Mm-hm.
One of the many reasons you
should formally join our agency.
You can continue to enjoy
all of their elite services.
Seriously?
Yes, of course.
Yumenosaki should be
providing these things.
Seems they're neglecting
you over there.
Huh?
That's not true.
Well, if you're happy,
that's all that matters.
But Cosmic Production
is always on the lookout
for shining stars like you.
[sighs] Well, it never
crossed my mind to leave,
but sounds like it's
worth thinking about.
I'll catch up with
you tomorrow morning.
[IBARA]
Take all the time you need,
and let the poison
seep in slowly.
By the time you realize
what is happening,
it'll be too late, Trickstar.
--[door opens]
--[SUBARU] Hello!
[MAO panting]
[GROUP gasps]
[panting]
What happened, Sally?
Did he do something to you?
[NAGISA]
Hmph. I haven't done a thing.
Hold on, aren't you Nagisa?
Nice to meet you!
I'm Akehoshi Subaru
from Trickstar!
And they are Ukki and Hokke!
[MAKOTO, HOKUTO grunt]
Can't wait to work
with you, jerk face!
What? You can't be
polite and attack someone!
You're getting weird, Akehoshi!
What the heck are you doing
to our friend, fine trash?
Why must you say that with
such spite, Masked Hokke?
Wait, you're Hidaka Hokuto.
And this must be Akehoshi
Subaru, Yuuki Makoto.
To me your names
are worth remembering.
However, the other one isn't.
[ALL gasp]
Overall, I can plainly see that
his skills are above average,
but his type and
personality are a dime a dozen.
[HOKUTO gasps]
[NAGISA] Eventually,
he won't be able to keep up
with the rest of you, and
he'll vanish or be forgotten.
[MAO gasps]
[NAGISA] But do try to
look on the bright side.
There are so many who
can easily replace him.
Don't beat yourself up
over a misunderstanding.
You're not the first to
see the glow of a flashlight
and mistake it for
the light of a real star.
[BOTH grunt]
Hey! Isara!
Was what I said really
that hard to comprehend?
I'll have to find a
better way to communicate.
Maybe I should
hire a translator.
[ALL grunting]
[TSUMUGI]
All right, here we are!
[SUBARU]
Wow!
It's so luxurious!
Sally! Look at this!
They made us welcome drinks!
Come on, let's throw 'em back!
Okay. Sure.
And if we get
a tatami-mat room,
we can have the
best pillow fight ever!
I'm so excited!
Are you sure we're
in the right place?
We're supposed to be at a hotel.
Yeah, Fushimi vetoed that idea,
and then he moved
our reservations here.
Good evening and welcome!
Fusshi!
Not only did he
supply this sweet upgrade,
he also came along
to show his support.
It's going to be a good week.
I look forward to
working with you.
Fushimi, are you
sure it's okay for us
to stay in such a nice place?
Yes, thanks to the president!
And he said we have the
whole place to ourselves.
Enjoy it and please don't
even worry about the cost.
But why would he
change the reservation?
The staff at this
inn are verified.
I assure you, they aren't
being controlled by our enemy.
As far as security goes, the
rooms have all been checked.
[gasps]
Have a good night and
please get some rest.
[SUBARU humming]
That felt so good!
There's even an open-air bath
in the room. It's amazing!
Wait, where's Sally?
I think he was going for a walk.
[SUBARU] Aww. We were all
supposed to have a pillow fight.
So look. I got tons.
[HOKUTO sighs]
You think he's okay? Be honest.
Yes, but I think he needs
time to process things.
After all the lessons I've
been forced to learn today,
I need some space
to think as well.
Wow, really?
Joining their agency
doesn't sound bad right now.
Yumenosaki has so many classes--
many that have
nothing to do with idols.
It feels like
a waste of time to me.
You're taking the bait
they set out for you.
Are you sure that's
how you actually feel?
Well, if I join the agency,
it doesn't mean I can't go
to Yumenosaki Academy anymore.
I think being in a good
environment is important.
It's necessary for growth.
But joining the
agency is very tempting.
Are you serious?
Under the circumstances, yes.
Maybe not if they asked us
to disband. Then I'd be out.
But it sounds like
they wanna be flexible
with the kind of work
we'd wanna take on.
Okay, stop!
Why is he talking
like that? What's going on?
Disband?
We only came here
to battle Adam. That's all!
[SUBARU sighs]
Normally, if things
started getting this tense,
Sally'd be here. He'd tell
a joke to make us laugh.
--[footsteps]
--[MAO grunts]
Hey, there you are.
He didn't really
say anything new.
I've known for a very long time.
The other Trickstar
members are truly gifted.
I'm not.
Didn't matter how hard I worked,
I never shined as
brightly as them.
And they knew it, too.
That's why I had to pretend
I wasn't really trying.
Like I didn't care
as much as I did.
When we fought Eve,
I wanted so badly to
show them what we could do.
But it wasn't enough.
[MAO sighs]
I wasn't enough.
They made fun of
Trickstar because of me.
Maybe I--
Maybe I'm bad for Trickstar.
[ANZU gasps]
That is not true!
Thank you.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Hey.
[RITSU] Sorry to bother ya.
Are you working?
[MAO]
Yeah, kinda. You okay, Ritsu?
Can you wake up on your own?
[RITSU]
I don't know.
But Knights is
running smoothly.
If you're not careful,
we might leave you in the dust.
[MAO gasps] Well, we can't
have that happen, now can we?
So I'll do my best.
What? Souvenirs?
Nah, I don't have time for that.
I'm getting ready for a concert!
[RITSU]
Aw, man, I wanted souvenirs.
Okay! Calm down.
I'll get you some. Come on!
[IBARA]
Not to worry, Your Excellency.
Everything is going as planned.
Don't concern yourself
with the Autumn Live.
Adam will shine brightly
all the way to victory.
What's more, our glory
will be so spectacular,
it can't even be
counted as competition.
[NAGISA]
Hmm.
Are you upset about something?
No.
Quite the opposite.
It's all because of you.
I can recognize the position
of everything in
this world instantly.
It's so easy.
Easy to plainly do as commanded.
I, Saegusa Ibara,
am committed to savoring all
the joys life has to offer.
The thing is, Your Excellency,
I am using you for
maximum possible benefit.
But I don't need
to tell you that.
I've no doubt that you're
completely aware already.
[NAGISA]
Hmph.
[TSUMUGI]
Anzu, over here!
Hello, and good morning!
Good morning to you!
And good morning, Isara.
[MAO chuckles]
[MAO] I'm making it my priority
to recover psychologically.
I had to leave Shuetsu.
Too many reminders of the
things that were said to me.
But if we're at Reimei Academy,
then we're here for Eve?
I don't think we know
anyone else here, do we?
Our goal for today is to
find a way to talk to Eve.
Even though Nagisa and I
are still pretty close,
we no longer go
to the same school.
--Right.
--Huh?
If we want to learn
more about Adam,
the fastest way
is just to ask Eve.
Know your enemy, know yourself,
and you shall not fear
a hundred battles, my friend.
[engine humming]
[gasps]
Whose car is that? It's nice.
That's Eve.
[door opens]