[SAGAMI]
Welcome to the DDD semifinal!
For the second match,
we have a showdown between...
...the unit, UNDEAD!
What do you think, Tenshouin?
This is pretty ironic, isn't it?
Everyone thought I was buried,
but I rose from
the dead like a demon,
and you, once known as Emperor,
are on your way to becoming
a dweller of the underworld.
And fine!
Is that so?
This is not the time to pretend
we're in an old Victorian drama.
[WATARU]
I agree!
And besides, it is almost time!
They've been waiting!
So let the curtain rise!
[WATARU]
This is like a battlefield
that will send us to Valhalla!
Dancing a bloody waltz
with a former friend
will also be most entertaining.
[WATARU]
Don't you think so, Rei?
[CROWD cheering]
Yes, I do. You're right.
'Course you'd say that.
You genius types
are all the same--
utterly impossible to deal with.
All right, we appreciate
your patience.
The next two units performing...
[BOTH]
...will now take the stage!
[CROWD cheering]
[MAO]
Hey, Mashiro.
You're in the same
club as Hokuto, right?
[TOMOYA]
Hmm?
[MAO]
Have you seen him around lately?
Ever since the DDD started
I haven't noticed him
anywhere around school.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I'm sure he's just working
extra hard on something.
[phone chimes]
[MAO]
I hope you're right.
Hi, Akehoshi, I have your
tea if you're ready for it.
[SUBARU]
You can just put it over there.
[HAJIME gasps]
Hey! I was only talking
to you like that as a joke!
I'm sorry, Shinonon! Don't cry!
[HAJIME chuckles]
Come on, let's go.
Don't bother him right now.
All the Trickstar
members are preparing
for their last big showdown.
'Kay. You're so right.
Besides, when he's
concentrating this hard,
he looks so dignified,
and, well, dreamy!
[NAZUNA] You never argue
about anything, do you?
How about you two?
Are you in the mood for tea?
Hey... Where'd Anzu go?
[MAO] Weird. She was
here just a minute ago.
So should we get
back to the auditorium?
Let's go!
My eyes will fall out
if they don't get
to see the match
between UNDEAD and fine!
[CROWD cheers]
[NAZUNA] It's going to be a
fierce battle, that's for sure.
Awesome!
This is the match of a lifetime!
[MITSURU]
We gotta get out there,
but break a leg Trickstar!
Yeah, if you guys
blow this final,
we're never gonna forgive you,
but that won't happen
'cause you're the best!
Uh, yeah!
You know it!
You're just gonna
ignore me, huh?
Well, fine.
I'll forgive you for
being rude just this once.
[NAZUNA] Let's hurry so
we can vote for UNDEAD
and get back at those
evil fine jerks!
--[MITSURU, TOMOYA] Yeah!
--[HAJIME] Yes!
Eichi!
What's wrong, President?
No!
What an amazing crowd!
We wish we could give
love to the whole world,
but for now,
we hope this will do!
[CROWD cheers]
The president is gonna die!
--[YUZURU] Keep your voice down.
--[TORI] Please let me be wrong!
These back-to-back performances
have caught up with me.
It looks like he's running out
of stamina up there, doesn't it?
I'm not surprised.
They've been fending off
back-to-back attacks
by so many strong units.
[EICHI] Sakuma Rei of the
Five--no, Three Eccentrics.
This is the first time
I've been cornered
by so many of my
opponents at once.
Consider it a retaliation from
those of us who gave
in to the tyranny.
You're a crafty one, aren't you?
I'm not sure why I'm surprised.
Thank you. I'm good.
When I was ill,
I'd lie in my hospital bed and
dream of standing on this stage.
Please don't push yourself.
We're fighting against
Trickstar in the final, right?
We couldn't lose
to them if we tried.
Thanks for making me laugh.
[EICHI] I've also exhausted each
member of fine in this process.
They've all been
working overtime
and offered me support
when I was too weak to stand.
I can't burden them any
more than I already have.
[EICHI]
Our first order of business...
...is to destroy UNDEAD!
Heh.
Then we'll give Trickstar what
they deserve and take the DDD.
The underdogs won't win!
A tragically heroic decision.
At last, pure intent
we can be proud of.
I must say,
it's amazing to witness!
I'll be watching
your performance
from right beside you.
Be sure to break legs
on your colorful and
exceptional tragicomedy!
[TORI]
Huh?
[EICHI]
He reminds me of Mephistopheles.
There are times
when you scare me.
But still, I'm going to need
your power if I want to win.
[EICHI] It looks like you
meddled in Hokuto's journey.
I'm too exhausted
to reprimand you,
so you're off the hook for now.
[WATARU] Oh, no, I better
watch my back, then!
I need to be more like
Chiaki from RYUSEITAI
and show these
underclassmen that I'm cool.
I am the president of the
theater club, after all.
Aren't you impressed?
Isn't this how you always
dreamed the events would unfold?
[buzzer sounds]
This is the end!
Whether we laugh or cry,
let's go all in!
[MAKOTO, MAO]
Yeah!
[KUNUGI]
UNDEAD versus fine.
After going into
overtime, the winner is...
[CROWD shouting]
[RA*BITS MEMBERS]
UNDEAD! UNDEAD!
[2WINK, RYUSEITAI MEMBERS]
[CROWD]
fine! fine! fine!
[CROWD screams]
[SAGAMI]
fine!
Congratulations to both units
on two wonderful performances!
Which means, the cards
for the final are...
...over there!
[TRICKSTAR MEMBERS gasp]
[IDOLS cheering]
What should we do?
Follow my lead! Yahoo!
--[MAKOTO] Hey!
--[MAO] Yeah!
[SUBARU]
Yeah!
Up we go!
[CROWD cheering]
Mr. President, we meet at last!
Aren't you the energetic one?
Thanks for your
hard work, Sakuma!
Well, sometimes
it doesn't pay off.
Unfortunately, we've been
eliminated from the battle.
You really wanted to win
this match, didn't you?
Maybe I did.
But my plan worked
perfectly, and I owe it all
to your willingness to grace
us with your presence, Kaoru.
I didn't do it for you, Sakuma.
I did it for the ladies
in the audience!
[CROWD screams]
Damn! This sucks!
I never said anyone could
stop singing and dancing!
Where did everybody go?!
[ADONIS] Go eat some
meat and have a rest.
See ya!
[KOGA]
Let go of me!
You must excuse us for now.
I wish you all the best of luck.
[EICHI chuckles]
Farewell. UNDEAD is
such a bothersome unit.
But you guys always look like
you're having so much fun.
I'm jealous.
[SUBARU]
What about you?
Aren't you having
fun, too, Eichi?
[EICHI]
Me?
Who knows?
Wait just a minute.
I have a question
before we start.
Where's Hokuto?
[EICHI] Perhaps you
should open your eyes.
Everything you're
looking for is here,
right in front of you.
Hokuto!
[MAO, MAKOTO gasp]
Hokuto.
It's you.
You're wearing...
your Trickstar outfit?
But wait...
...you joined with fine and
the student council president!
It's not like that.
Listen to me.
[TORI]
No one has to listen to you,
you traitor monster idiot!
[SAGAMI] And now,
before the final starts,
we'll have to
take a short break.
[HOKUTO] It took me a long
time to make my decision,
but since the semifinal
went into overtime,
it gave me the chance.
I don't normally think
I live a very good life,
but once in a while,
I'm blessed with good fortune.
[SUBARU]
That's not what I mean!
[HOKUTO]
I'm sorry.
I know I might
not have the right
to wear these clothes
anymore, but still.
[SUBARU]
Aw, jeez, I'm trying to say--
So you choose to walk
the path of thorns, then?
I hope you don't expect
your parents to be proud.
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
His parents?
[HOKUTO]
I get it now.
You used your status
and power to make my parents
want me to be in your circle.
They want me to obey the son
of the Tenshouin Conglomerate--
not because it'd be good for me,
but because you
manipulated them!
Hokke.
[HOKUTO]
With that...
...you made the decision
to join your unit for me.
And, yet, how could
I be happy if I betrayed
my friends to gain
my parents' acceptance?
[ANZU, MAO, MAKOTO, SUBARU gasp]
I almost ruined everything--
destroyed what
mattered most to me.
I was a fool, but I didn't
quite understand that,
not until I read
my grandma's letter.
Oh, yes, that letter, right?
Are you going to
tell us what it said?
Nothing special.
Just a message from
grandmother to grandson.
[HOKUTO crying]
[HOKUTO] She said
I don't always have to do
what everyone tells me to,
that I should do
the things I wanna do.
[HOKUTO]
Grandma!
And no matter what happens...
Is this candy for me?
[HOKUTO]
...she's always on my side.
Grandma's not an idol or an
actress or anything like that.
She's a regular person
you'd see anywhere.
But I love her so much!
And if she's on my side,
then I can fight proudly.
I remember who I am now.
Trickstar is where I belong!
Hokuto!
--[HOKUTO] But...
--Uh?
I don't think I have the right
to go back to you guys yet!
Not unless--no.
Never mind, I'm so stupid.
If only--!
[SUBARU] Well, I've got
a question I want you to answer!
--Oh my god!
--What took you so long?!
He punched him?
[HOKUTO chuckles]
Keep punching me, Akehoshi.
I deserve it for all
the evil I've committed,
even if today
is our last concert.
Why is Hidaka suddenly
acting weird, too?
This isn't our "last" anything.
We're still the best unit ever.
That includes you.
Thank you.
[EICHI]
Too bad.
[HOKUTO]
Is that--?
It's your contract to join fine.
I could make you do anything
with this if I wanted to.
But...
...I'm the student
council president.
With that authority,
I'm releasing you of
your commitment, Hokuto.
[EICHI] But in exchange,
I won't go easy on you.
[HOKUTO]
I wouldn't want you to.
[EICHI]
That's the spirit.
Shall we begin the performance?
I think it's time now.
Let's make our ensemble resound!
[CROWD cheering]
[SAGAMI]
Thanks for waiting!
Who's ready to get
this final started?
[KUNUGI]
First turn.
Isara Mao versus Hibiki Wataru.
Ready, go!
Heh. Hibiki Wataru?
They're putting me up against
one of the Three Eccentrics?
[WATARU laughs]
I'm ready to give them the
best performance of our lives!
Well, that makes two of us!
This is going to be amazing!
Gotta say, that
Isara kid's not bad.
And he's up against Sir Hibiki.
[KUNUGI]
Second turn.
Hidaka Hokuto
versus Fushimi Yuzuru!
I applaud and support your bold
choice tonight, Master Hidaka.
I thought you'd accuse
me of betraying you
like any self-respecting
butler would.
You are bound to nobody but
the commands of your own heart.
You watch. I'm about
to entertain you
and the audience together!
Good job!
That's the spirit!
[KUNUGI] Third! Yuuki Makoto
versus Himemiya Tori!
[TORI]
Great. This is too easy.
Guess I won't be bragging
to the president when I win!
[MAKOTO] Is he saying
something mean to me?
I'll show you, kid!
Just you wait!
Ow! Rude! What's your
problem, scumbag?
Why are you trying to harass me?
I'm an idol, too, ya know!
[BOTH grunting]
What the heck is happening?
[KUNUGI]
Last up!
Akehoshi Subaru
versus Tenshouin Eichi!
How does it feel to be
the opening tribute act
to a beloved emperor?
You won't be able to stay up
on that high horse
of yours for very long!
[EICHI]
If I can capture this dream,
then I'll become even stronger!
The underdogs will win
and start a revolution!
You don't know what
it's like at the top!
Tomorrow Yumenosaki Academy
will be an entirely new place!
Everyone will be
smiling and happy!
That's what I came for!
[CROWD cheering]
They shine...
...so brilliantly.
[CROWD cheering]
[GROUP panting]
[SUBARU]
I went all out!
[GROUP panting]
[EICHI]
Stand up. You're still on stage.
You must show
dignity at all times,
or at least until
the curtain falls.
What about you, Mr. President?
Are you feeling any better?
I'm not so sure.
It's kind of late to ask,
but why did you
decide to have the DDD?
Couldn't fine have represented
the school at the SS
without you pushing
yourself to such extremes?
[chuckles]
That's a very good question.
I don't know for sure.
I suppose I wanted
to see a miracle happen.
There's power in the
way you shine on stage.
It could change a fate
that was set in stone.
I was born with
this weakened body.
I cursed God many times.
And yet, if there are still
miracles in this world--
if there are hopes, and
dreams, and love left here...
...then maybe I can
also accept my fate.
You cannot become an
idol with just love alone,
but without that love
you won't succeed.
Honestly, all I wanted
was to simply be an idol.
[MEMBERS gasp]
Can you hear me?
You okay, President?
I think I understand
how he feels.
I also want to be an idol in
the purest sense of the word.
Everyone in the idol course
at Yumenosaki feels that way.
So you're just like
the rest of us! Heh, heh!
You think so?
I guess that might be the case.
[EICHI]
Yes.
I'm sure it's true.
We will now announce the
results of the DDD final match!
After tallying up the votes...
[KUNUGI]
...the winner is fine!
[CROWD shouting]
[SUBARU gasps]
Well, it looks like
we lost this one.
[KUNUGI] Hang on, folks.
It's not over yet.
According to the rules, if
a unit wins by a small margin
the stipulation is that there
will be an overtime match.
In the final results,
fine did receive
more votes than Trickstar, true,
but those votes were
within the percentage
that trigger a rematch.
Does this mean what I think?
[SAGAMI]
What do you wanna do, Tenshouin?
Play the extra match?
[CROWD] fine! Trickstar!
fine! Trickstar!
No, thanks. I think
it's time to end this.
Is that all right with you?
Of course, if that is
your wish, President.
But, if we don't
play, then we--
Amazing! Wow! So congrats!
We have a definitive
winner of the final match,
and it's you, Trickstar!
[TRICKSTAR MEMBERS gasping]
[MAKOTO]
What?
[CROWD cheering]
[SUBARU, MAO yell]
[MAKOTO]
Seriously? All right!
[HOKUTO]
We actually did it!
We pulled off our revolution!
[SUBARU]
Thanks so much!
Are you sure this is okay?
You don't want to
change your mind?
Of course.
I'm a little
disappointed though.
Look.
Your bond was on
the verge of breaking,
but that girl wove
it back together
and led you all to this point.
--[MAO, MAKOTO, HOKUTO chuckle]
--[SUBARU] Anzu!
Oh, hey, wait up you guys!
You can't just
run off like that!
We're not done here!
Have you all forgotten?
We have an encore!
The winning unit
is supposed to perform!
So do it. We're
not stopping you.
There are so many things
I want to learn from you!
Will you teach me?
Teach you?
You were kind to your enemy
and asked for my help.
I could learn from you, too.
So that's where your
strength comes from--
your heart.
I'd like to be strong like you.
And next time, we should
have more matches
that challenge us to bare
the contents of our souls.
[SUBARU]
Mm-hm.
[EICHI] I'm truly glad
that I met you all.
Yeah, me, too!
[CROWD]
Trickstar!
There's no way we
could've done this alone!
We're truly grateful
to our producer,
Anzu, and everyone
who has supported us!
So for this next song we
need you guys to sing along!
[RYUSEITAI MEMBERS]
Oh, yeah!
[IDOLS]
Yeah!
[TSUMUGI]
Why aren't you singing, Eichi?
[gasps] Tsumugi?
Woo-hoo!
The singing sounded so fun,
we had to come watch.
I know you worked hard.
You did a great job.
Well, thanks. That means a lot.
[ANZU]
This is Yumenosaki Academy.
The name says it all.
It's a school where
dreams come true!
[ANZU] The time for
revolution has ended,
and now we make way for
the brand new season to come.