Stop running, goddammit!
Yeah, like I'm gonna stop
'cause you fuckin' told me to!
Son of a bitch!
Sorry, asshole. Game over.
What the fuck...
The fuck is that?
Stop...! I give up okay?!
"Yeah, like I'm gonna stop...
'cause you fucking' told me to!"
Senji! Enough!
You're a damn cop now...
You can't just kill people.
You lucked out, asshole.
♪ opening song ♪
What're the odds of that...?!
That bastard knew we
were staking him out...!
It's almost like somebody
told 'em we were comin'!
C'mon, I don't
even know the guy!
Okay, who gave that fucker
the heads-up, then...?! Huh?!
Aaaw, give it a rest, Senji...
You probably told
him your damn self.
Huh...? The hell you say?
Sounds right to me...
He probably he caught wind of it
from his old pal, Officer Senji.
You're a cop now...
But don't think sporting a badge
automatically means your
past ain't fair game...
What'd you say?!
You... asshole...!
Jeez, you never learn, do ya...
I mean...
you always end up getting in
someone's face about something,
and then you go right
for the left hook.
You're wasting
your breath, man...
Trying to reason with him is
like talking to a damn wall.
Yeah, I know, but...
if he keeps raising hell,
they'll rake us over the
coals on our next write-up.
Well... at least you
know he's got grit!
That's great...
but he keeps tracking
it into the precinct...
[loud thud]
What's up with you, Senji?
Something wrong?
Can't breathe is all...
Feels like I'm choking.
Want me to crack a
window or something?
I'm taking a walk.
Hey... Where're you going?
Huh...?
Looks like the Chief
tore ya a new asshole.
Yeah, more o' less...
He seems to think that Senji is
more trouble than he's worth.
That's pretty tough
talk from a man
who's up to his
nostrils in graft.
You did this to yourself
when you brought in
that stray of yours,
Domon ol' pal...
You get to clean up after him.
Yeah, so I did...
Us old farts always have
to look after the young'uns.
Wait... isn't that...?
A couple o' thugs
from Goreless Peace.
I never heard of 'em.
They're a gang...
Been calling themselves
the neighborhood watch...
but all they ever watch
out for is our money...
Criminals, every one of 'em.
Ain't the only gang...
but they're the worst.
No! Leggo, you jerk!
What's the big idea...?!
Well... seems we got
ourselves a little thief.
Kid's got balls,
liftin' with us around.
I betcha can't steal
one-handed...
Only one way to find out...
I only gotta...
'cause you guys have been
squelching all the rations...!
Sons o' bitches!
I'm sorry...!
I didn't quite catch that...
Who'd you say are
sons o' bitches?!
You dumb-shits.
What the fu--?!
Holy shit, look at the
size of that knife...!
Wait a sec... that's
not a knife, is it...?
Honestly? I don't know what
the hell this is either...
All I know for sure...
...is that it cuts through trash
like you real fucking good!
It hurts... Oh man, it hurts...!
C'mon...! You'll get
yours later, pig!
You're the man, Senji!
You're damn right I am.
Hey.
Izuru...!
What have you
gotten into now...?!
I'm sorry, Senji, I should have
watched him more carefully--
Hey, it's all good...
Just ground his ass... Go.
Don't tell me you
were stealing again.
Yes, ma'am...
I'm sorry, Miss Hinata.
Hinata!
Damn... So he stole
a little--calm down...!
Why are you defending him?!
I... I'm sorry.
Wow, I just yelled at a cop...!
Nah... it's okay...
Just don't hit me...
I just dunno how you do it...
I'm serious, Hinata...
Taking in all these
street kids...?
And paying for it outta
pocket like ya do...?
Please, it's not like
I'm some sort of saint...
I mean...
part of the reason I'm doing
all this is out of vengeance.
Vengeance, huh?
Two years, it's been...
since the day that the
earthquake changed everything...
But still...
We can't stop
being decent people
just 'cause we got the rug
yanked out from under us...
Now more than ever,
I'm not going to let those
kids slip through the cracks.
If I can keep them
safe and happy...
It kinda feels like...
I'm flipping off the quake.
Flippin' it off... Huh.
That's right...
Show it who's boss!
Uh-huh!
Man, it got hot all of a sudden!
You hot? 'Cause I'm sweatin'!
Oh yeah?
Someday I'm gonna be
strong as you, Senji!
Keep dreaming, kid...
This bad-ass is one of a kind.
I'll be... like... the
defender of the orphanage!
Be a cop...
You get free tomatoes.
Very interesting weaponry...
You're Senji Kiyomasa,
aren't you?
Keigo Ugachi is the name...
I take it you're familiar
with our little organization.
Think of me as Goreless
Peace's liaison.
It's precisely as I thought...
Our souls are simpatico!
Afraid not!
Well, my dear Senji...
I have an offer for you...
Would you care to help me
re-tune this atonal world?
"Re-tune?"
The Red Hole shook this
town--this whole world--
and everything's been
out of key ever since...
So I'm going to tighten
the proverbial strings.
And as soon everything is
pitch-perfect once again...
the song I play upon it
will be a thing of beauty!
You're an idiot.
That uniform looks
pretty... constricting.
What the fuck...?!
It must be a ball, officer...
Making sure your necktie
is tied just right...
Licking the boot soles of
those who lord above you...
Dealing with the
dregs of humanity,
day after
soul-crushing day...!
The very thought of it
sets my head a-throbbing!
Whereas I... am
with Goreless Peace.
We're working towards an
idyllic world for all to enjoy.
But somebody has to tighten
the strings first, don't they?
Is that why you beat
up little kids...?
Because it's all part
of your Kumbaya crap?
Re-tuning can be physical.
In time, I'm sure
you'll see it my way.
We're simpatico.
Bastard...!
I'll cut off your goddamn mouth!
You're a rare bird
indeed, Senji...
I do look forward to
our next conversation.
Yeah, blow it out your ass.
Stupid kid...!
Giving me unripe tomatoes...!
You're pretty green yourself,
so what's the problem?
Another coffin-nail, huh...?
That shit's gonna kill you,
ya know that, right?
There's not much a man calls
the shots on these days...
but his death is
still one of 'em.
Whole damn world's going
down the crapper...
We lock these fuckers up,
and for what?
Somebody's gotta give
the ol' girl a scrub...
The world needs fools like us...
Like you, Senji.
Tell me something, old man...
What made you think I'd
be worth a damn at this?
If it's heads, you walk the beat
tomorrow and I play solitaire...
If it's tails, you sleep in.
Hey, looks like
it's heads... Huh?
Why, you cheating
son of a bitch!
And grab some of those for me
while you're out
and about, okay...?
I mean, if...
you're gonna stop by.
Huh...?
Damn...
You just think ya know
everything--dontcha, old man!
Oh, yes...
I find him intriguing,
albeit brutish...
And, if he doesn't come
'round on his own...
I'll think of something.
Yes... Yes, you're
quite right, Mr. Akatsuki.
Senji's one of us...
but he has yet to
arrive at that truth.
What am I grinning about...?
just going to see a bunch
of snot-nosed brats.
[siren wails]
God... They were just... kids...
Hinata!
Say something... Please!
Izuru...! You gotta hold on...!
Don't you die on me.
I could've... saved 'em...
if I'd just been...
as strong as you are, Senji...
Come on...
Just open your eyes...
Open your eyes, dammit!
Senji, come in...!
I know you can
hear me, dammit...!
Talk to me...!
I'm here.
Look, son...
You gotta come back!
No...
Not before I kill all
those motherfuckers.
You're not a killer!
Why, 'cause I'm a cop...?
Then you can have
my fucking badge...
But I gotta do this.
Goddamn it...
Goreless Peace?
The dude's toast.
That dumbshit.
Easier to leave 'em be.
Get himself a little
spending money...
I'm not gonna lie,
I'm glad the fucker's out...
He never was a team player.
You watch your damn mouth!
Hell, we can cook
up the paperwork.
"Check it out, guys, is
that a gang fight I hear?"
And our write-ups
can suck a dick.
Yeah, suck a big one!
Look at ya...
What the hell am I gonna
do with this buncha lugs?
Our guest of honor
has arrived...
This mutton I've procured for
our meal is simply to die for.
The younger the lamb,
the richer the blood, they say.
I trust that you happened upon
the invitation I left you.
Those orphans were a
millstone tied to your neck...
but now you are free to
join us without hesitation.
Alas...
Our world is so cacophonous,
it turns my stomach.
Take friendship...
or legends like
compassion and honor...
Or even that old wives
tale, true love...
You're far too magnificent
to be hampered by all that.
Not you, O Righteous Wielder
of the Crimson Blades...
...who's murdered dozens
in the blink of an eye.
We are birds of a feather,
you and I...!
Now...! Let us plan
our conquest...!
We will tune this
world togeth--!
I didn't come here to join your
new-world-order marching band...
I came here to kill your ass.
What a terrible shame...
I figured that you...
would understand me.
Like hell are we letting
you do this by yourself.
There's ten of these goons
for every one of us.
We'll take 'em on an
illegal weapons charge.
You guys are screwwwed!
Aw shit!
Ugachi! Show yourself!
What the hell?
Come now, Senji.
I said we were simpatico.
You bastard...!
Like those pesky orphans
we had to massacre,
you are simply too loud.
Oh hush, now...
I've had enough
screaming for today.
Those caterwauling brats
put my stomach on edge!
Do you know what a perfect
melody would sound like?
It would sound like nothing.
Like order itself.
The music of the spheres...!
This would be a world
in which silence swells
to a deafening crescendo!
Fuck your melody...!
I'm gonna cut you in half!
And you'll be doing that how?
Why even try...?
My crimson cords will transfix
you fast where you stand...
Within the Wire Lyre!
Mine don't have some
pussy-ass nickname...!
But they still get the job done!
See...? You can't even get
within slicing range.
Senji!
How barbaric...!
You just barrel in during
my pièce de résistance...!
Old man!
I'll just usher you
out... of life!
What?!
You mean to kill me...
Just get on with it, then.
Well...? What are
you waiting for, Senji?
Send me to the abyss.
Stand down!
Don't you listen to him...
Damn it, son...
If you kill this fucker,
you're no better than he is!
Yeah, I know.
You're a fool.
Senji!
Huh...?
You flinched...
It's tough bringing
'em up right.
So... Ogachee's in
police custody...
Yes... I understand.
Senji Kiyomasa...
I wonder if you will
stand with me someday...
or against me?
Gonna be privatized--
that the word?
Uh-huh.
The times, they are
a-changing, fellas...
Theme park vibe or not,
it's still gonna be full
of the same ol' shit.
And we're the lucky schmucks
who get to put 'em in there.
You heard him, ladies...
Back to work.
--Yeah.
--Fine.
Old man!
Huh?
Oh! Son-of-a...! What the...?
These're ready now.
♪ closing song ♪