[DIRECTOR]
You'll be pleased...
I picked up more of that
delightful pudding...
There on the hidden shelf,
as it ever sits.
[SHIRO] Pudding makes
me want to vomit.
It's Shiro that has
the sweet-tooth, not me.
Yes, yes...
of course she does...
Well then...
shall we begin, my child?!
Now let us continue
to kill each other...
and perish in turn!
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[DIRECTOR GRUNTS]
♪ opening song ♪
[GANTA] Hey Yoh...
Are you doing okay?
[YOH] Yeah.
Man, she really did
a number on you.
Nah, I'm good...
Shoulda eaten more
before the fight, though...
I got a little bit
anemic out there.
I'm sorry, man...
I didn't know she
was your little sis.
Ever since Mom died
a couple years back...
I've tried to...
protect her.
[RUMBLING]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[CLATTERING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[YOH GASPS]
Minatsuki, no!
[MINATSUKI GASPS]
[CHILD YOH GRUNTS]
Sis!
You're safe now...!
[CHILD MINATSUKI]
Big brother...
[CRASHING SOUND]
Holy crap...!
Look at your arm...
That's gotta hurt...!
What... this...?
It's just a little scratch.
[YOH WINCES]
[MINATSUKI] That's more
than a little scratch!
What in the hell
were you thinking?!
Just... that I'm
your big brother.
You asshole...!
Careful...! Don't just
go yanking 'em out!
[GLASS SHATTERS]
You guys're weird...
Hey, I remember
that scent...
You smell
like primroses.
I'm sorry... I haven't
been there for you...
but I promise...
from here on out...
I'll protect you.
[MINATSUKI]
I can protect myself.
I always have...
What happened to Dad
that day was all my fault!
You couldn't have known...
about the branches of sin...
or all of the damage
they could cause...
Nobody could have predicted
all the crap that went down...
so you aren't to blame.
So fucking what?!
I still killed him, didn't I?!
[GANTA THINKING]
How come... my chest hurts?
[Instrumental "Lullaby"]
White hair...
[GANTA GASPS]
No way... That girl...
it was Shiro...
[Instrumental
"Lullaby" continues]
[SHIRO]
I can hear the lullaby.
Does that mean the Mother Goose
System's up and running again?
How does the rest go?
[DIRECTOR]
Rest, you say...?
There isn't any...
There can...
never be more of it.
Behold... the Wretched Egg.
The abandoned one...
You are as the world
has made you.
[GUARD 7-A] I want a damage
report... floor by floor!
[GUARD 7-B] Wire us
into the auxiliary power!
C'mon! Hurry it up!
Looks like this area
got hit just as bad...
[GUARD 7-A] The injured
are gonna have to wait...!
You...! Outta the way!
[GANTA YELLS]
[SENJI]
'Sup, Woodpecker?
Hey Senji!
That fight had me on
the edge of my seat...
And your head-butt
was fuckin' legit.
Huh? Hey, what's the matter?
[GANTA] I'm sorry
about your eye...
You lost it...
'cause of me...
Huh?
[SENJI LAUGHS]
Crap like that goes down
here all the time...
Don't let it get to you.
But it does!
[SENJI] I know
you're winnin', but...
...you gotta mix
it up out there.
You can't keep spamming the
same move like a one-trick pony.
What do you mean?
Using the Ganta Gun
for everything.
The...
Ganta Gun...?
That's what folks're
calling your blood attack...
Bad-ass, huh?
I coined it myself.
Uh... it is... But if
we're gonna name it...
maybe we could go
with something like...
Uh, how 'bout... Yeah!
How 'bout we
make it sound like
an attack name
from "Aceman"!
"Visco-Elastic
Soldier Aceman," huh?
That takes me back.
I'm surprised
you're a fan...
Before your day,
wasn't it?
[GANTA] Yeah, but
I caught 'em on video...
I remember playing
Aceman all the time
with this one friend of
mine when I was little...
Man, we had so much fun.
Beat the snot out
of each other...!
Well, at least...
she beat it outta me...
[YOH SCREAMS]
No, you've got it all wrong!
I was just worried
about your injuries! Ahh!
[MINATSUKI]
Blow it out your ass!
I wasn't born yesterday!
None of my injuries
are so bad that
I can't take a friggin'
shower by myself, Yoh!
Just leave me alone...
for ten minutes!
Don't look at my tits!
[SENJI GROANS]
[GANTA] Senji...
are you...?
I'm okay...
I wanted... to tell ya...
Mad props... That was
one helluva head-butt, dude!
[GANTA] So, uh... how's Shiro
been since we got split up?
You were with her, right?
[YOH] Yeah, but only until
I snuck back into G Block.
[GANTA] I see...
[YOH]
Hey Ganta...
Huh?
[YOH]
That girl... Who is she?
[GANTA] Who, Shiro...?
Y'know, it's kinda weird...
I'd forgotten until just now,
but me and her actually
used to know each other.
My mom was still
alive back then, so...
ten years ago, at least.
[CHILD GANTA LAUGHS]
[CHILD GANTA]
Heya, Shiro!
Guess what?!
I brought snacks!
Pudding!
Not hungry.
[CHILD SHIRO]
I dunno how come,
but my hands and feet
have been hurting a lot...
And all those stupid shots...
I'm so sick of it!
[CHILD GANTA]
No one told you the secret?
Huh...?
Whenever something real
bad happens to you...
you just gotta call "Aceman!"
and he'll come save ya!
"Aceman?"... Oh, Ganta,
he's just a guy on TV.
[CHILD GANTA]
First name Ace, last name Man!
He's the hero with the plan!
Shiro's pain will run away!
Don't worry, kid,
I'll save ya...!
Time for... my Ultra-Chaos
Endorphin Rush!
[CHILD SHIRO]
Knock it off!
[CHILD SHIRO] It's not Shiro's
fault your stupid toy broke!
[CHILD GANTA]
I'll go eat by myself...
[CHILD GANTA CRIES]
[CHILD GANTA] Why's she
being such a butthead?
Mommy...?
[DOG GROWLS]
[CHILD GANTA YELLS]
[CHILD GANTA]
Hey! That's my pudding!
[DOG GROWLS]
[CHILD GANTA YELLS]
Somebody, help me!
Aceman! Aceman...! Aceman!
[DOG CRIES]
[CHILD SHIRO] Ta da.
Shiro...?
[CHILD SHIRO]
Aceman is on the scene.
[CHILD GANTA LAUGHS]
[GANTA] She's always
been like that, huh...
Popping in right when
I need her the most...
I can't believe
I forgot her...
I should say I'm sorry.
But I wonder... where
does Shiro usually stay?
What if...
she was...
I want to
see her again.
[KASUGA] Any time we try to
access sensitive information
about Deadman Wonderland,
we get this password prompt,
courtesy of Mr. Tamaki.
Unfortunately, it's ground our
Necro Macro
investigation to a halt.
And as you can see here...
we're also stuck with the
guard tower investigation--
[LOUD THUD]
[MAKINA] The tremor that
hit us a few minutes ago
was no regular earthquake.
This was the epicenter...
Awfully convenient that
Deadman Wonderland was
ground zero for a
gravitational anomaly.
This ringing a bell
with anyone else?
Ten years ago...
the Red Hole quake
tore open Tokyo right here.
I am the Chief Warden of this
prison, ladies and gentlemen...
And secrets are
being withheld from me.
I'm going to get to the
bottom of this situation...
if I have to carve through
this place, block by block!
[GUARDS] Ahh...
And if you lack the balls
to help me clean
this facility up...
get the fuck out of my way!
[CRASHING SOUND]
Watch your ass, Tamaki!
I've got the
heebie-jeebies...
Not fun...
If only one of those eggheads
would answer the phone...
So...! What's young master
Ganta sporting in his sternum?
[TAKASHIMA] Sir, the red
crystal that's lodged
within the boy's chest
is a type of capsule.
It's an aggregation... a sliver,
of the Nameless Worm virus.
It matches the viral
shards that were found
after the Red Hole
quake ten years ago.
Those pieces have all
gone inert long since,
while the one inside
5580 is still quite active.
[TAKASHIMA LIGHTS CIGARETTE]
That said... at least
we've figured out
why the branches of sin
are unique to individuals
who were in the Kanto region
when the quake struck...
It's better than nothing.
I can't say
how they did it...
All I know is that
the crystals found their way
inside the subjects
and infected them.
[TAMAKI] Illuminating.
But riddle me this...
Can we infect people ourselves?
Uh... the Nameless Worm virus
isn't something we can
cook up in a Petrie dish.
The Wretched Egg
is hands-off,
and he's our Patient Zero.
Ugh...
He's my dad's toy.
In the five years
I've been here,
I've never even seen
what's under his mask...
Tried hacking the data...
but Pops has cyber-security
that would put the
Pentagon to shame...
Why have such a
great action figure
if you're going to keep
it sealed in the box?
Speaking of Dad...
I don't know
what's behind it...
but he's getting
old very fast.
[TAMAKI] At the rate
he's wasting away...
it won't be very long now.
There'll be some
changes around here
when I'm running the show!
[GANTA] Yoh, I--!
[GANTA STAMMERS]
I'm gonna strangle you
with my damn bra!
[GANTA]
I totally forgot!
About what?
Aren't they gonna
make you play a...
...a penalty round?
Heh... That's just how
we roll in Wonderland.
I've already popped
my penalty cherry,
unlike someone I know...
Already lost half my
stomach and a kidney.
But... but you can't
keep going through that!
[MINATSUKI] Huh...
Enough is enough, Minatsuki!
[MINATSUKI LAUGHS]
That's what big brother told me
right before he ran outta here!
That, and some bullshit
about how he was gonna
get his cast points back?
[GANTA]
Oh! That's right!
[MINATSUKI]
Wait... What?
What's the deal
with these guys?
I mean chill the fuck out.
[GANTA THINKING] If he buys
out the rest of her sentence,
then there's no penalty game!
[GANTA GRUNTS IN PAIN]
What the... hell?!
[KARAKO]
Oh... My bad!
I kinda figured
you'd dodge it.
[TAMAKI] As I live and
breathe... it's Yoh!
What a coincidence...
Do explain your presence.
[YOH] I'm keeping tabs
on Ganta, like you told me.
[TAMAKI] So I did.
Well... no harm
done, I suppose.
Huh...? Is that a monk?
[GENKAKU] C'mon...
Don't sell me short, bro.
I'm an uber-monk.
[YOH THINKING] Who the hell
does this jackass think he is?
If he's the one who
cares for our souls,
we're screwed in death, too.
[GENKAKU YAWNS]
By the way... a word
to the wise, Yoh...
Buying things with cast points
works a little differently
down here ol' G Block way.
For example, you
aren't going to find
"buying out a sentence"
on the menu.
What did you say?!
[TAMAKI]
Now run along!
Don't want to miss your little
sister's penalty spin, do you?
[YOH THINKING] I... I can't buy
Minatsuki her freedom...?!
All those cast points...
and for what?!
[TAMAKI] I wonder
what she'll lose?
Tip of her little
nose? A whole leg?
Or maybe one of those
mysterious lady-bits...!
You asshole!
[GENKAKU]
Power-chord!
[YOH YELLS]
[THUD]
Don't trouble yourself
with him... good Genkaku.
This one isn't a deadman. Alas.
The deadmen have gotten
too big for their britches...
I'm heading off to
the laboratory for a bit.
Be a dear and take
care of them, would you?
[GENKAKU]
Command performance, huh?
Hell... guess I'll grace 'em
with a song or two...
Really sorry I
kicked your ass, kid.
I just wanted to see what
all the fuss was about.
Well... I guess I'm too
strong for ya, short stuff.
Case closed.
My name's
Karako Koshio.
Scar Chain could
use a guy like you.
[GANTA] Wha...?
So... you wanna help us
fight the good fight?
Huh...?! I'm still working on
the part where you hit me...
And what's a Scar Chain?
[NAGI] I figured you'd
be open to our cause.
It's a pleasure, Ganta.
I probably should've
explained our group
before asking
you to join us...
We're known as Scar Chain.
We're a band of rebels...
And I'm Nagi, its leader.
[GANTA THINKING]
Rebels? And that voice...!
This prison's existence
is a miscarriage of justice.
The Director dreamed
up this hell-hole...
and his son, the Promoter,
makes it even worse.
Scar Chain is going to
destroy this funhouse
from the inside out.
[NAGI]
Now more than ever,
we're in need of new
blood just to even the odds.
[KARAKO]
I saw your fight yesterday and
I had to pass your name
along to Nagi here.
Told him you had balls like
nobody's business... Right?
[NAGI] Indeed...
Those were the very
words she used.
So you're gonna destroy it?!
[GANTA THINKING]
Good to know they get how
effed up this place is...
I thought I was
the odd man out...
Oh...! Yeah, actually,
can I get back to you?!
It's just I'm in a big
hurry at the moment!
[KARAKO AND NAGI]
Huh...?
Well, because I won
my match yesterday,
there's supposed to
be a penalty round,
and I'm trying to
find a way to stop it.
[TV TURNS ON]
[MUSIC PLAYS ON TV]
Oh no ya don't...!
[NAGI] Concern for a fallen
foe. That's a rare quality.
Huh...?
This is Owl, over.
[TAKASHIMA]
It's been too long, Minatsuki!
Let's see what I get
to pull out of you today?
Maybe I'll luck out and
you'll roll something
you can be awake
for this time...!
Better cross your
fingers, cunt-face!
[TAKASHIMA]
You sound kind of worried...
Did I strike a nerve?
You look like your
ready to piss yourself.
[MINATSUKI] I'm fine!
[MINATSUKI THINKING] This isn't
like me. What the hell...?!
It's my dumbass
brother and that kid...
acting all decent and shit.
Fuck sanity...
it's not healthy.
Don't think...
Don't be afraid...
When that whore comes
over with her scalpel...
you just laugh in
her goddamn face!
Pull it already!
[CLANKING SOUNDS]
[MINATSUKI]
Big brother...
[TAKASHIMA GASPS]
Personally, I find short hair
on a woman very attractive...
but your mileage may vary.
[TAKASHIMA]
What the hell?!
Hair is not supposed to
be one of choices, dammit!
[MINATSUKI LAUGHS]
She rolled hair...!
She ain't out of
the woods just yet...
Better hope that
dumbass doctor doesn't
yank it out
by the handful.
Man...! I thought
she was a goner!
That's about as much
as we can manage...
But if it allows you to
have faith in what we do...
We would be honored
to count you among those
who are lending their
strength to our plans.
What kinda plans?
[GENKAKU]
God, what a stench!
Your blood reeks, y'know that?
Now, now. Don't everyone
get up all at once...
Rush the stage,
and you might end up...
like this poor music fan...
[THUD]
Oh my god...
that's Yoh!
You thug...!
[KARAKO] I'm gonna shove that
guitar right up your ass!
[KARAKO YELLS]
[NAGI] Karako!
[GANTA]
Why did you do this?
Who the hell are you?
Answer me!
Just your standard uber-monk...
I'm concerned
for your soul...
How it's stuck... in that
meat-sack of a body.
Whaddya say I let it out?
[GANTA] Whaddya say
I kick your ass?!
[GANTA SCREAMS]
No... Ganta!
[GENKAKU] I see a new face
in the audience. Heh, Heh...
This song's for you, kid.
My attack didn't
even touch him!
Go, Ganta...
Run away...!
[GUITAR SOUNDS]
Down for a duet, 'cause
I'm ready to shred!
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA] You've discovered
the resistance movement
within the prison, Ganta.
If their jailors sit back
and let them try to escape...
Then the rules of the
game have changed...
and you're all
playing for keeps.