[BEEPING AND WHIRRING]
Shiro!
[EXPLOSION]
[SHIRO YELLS]
Dead center.
[BEEPING AND WHIRRING]
[SENJI]
'Bout damn time...
I've been waiting for them
to reactivate you...
Don't think I've forgotten
the last time we had
a little one on one.
[CRASHING SOUND]
That felt great...
Just what I needed.
It's him...
It's the Red Man.
Heh...
[GANTA GASPS]
I don't... I don't believe it.
[GANTA GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[YOH] Ganta!
[GANTA YELLS]
Wait a minute;
is that him?
You gotta be kidding me.
[GANTA YELLS ANGRILY]
[SENJI] Heh. So the Woodpecker
couldn't wait till tomorrow...
[GANTA YELLS]
What the hell...?
Is that... his blood?
Branch of Sin...
Crow Claw...
[GANTA GROANS IN PAIN]
♪ opening song ♪
[SNAKE]
Say what you will,
the last Carnival Corpse was
worth losing my shirt over.
[BUNNY] Ugh! I practically
gnawed my cuticles down to nubs
I threw so much in...
[BEAR] Heh, heh...
I'm with you there.
What do you think
tomorrow's going to be like
when they unveil
the newcomer...? Huh?
[TAMAKI] Indeed...
Particularly considering he's
slated to wrangle with the Crow.
[SNAKE] Sounds like there's
going to be fireworks.
My wife's a huge
Crow fan, you know...
[TAMAKI] Believe me, I'm as
breathless with anticipation
as the rest of you.
[DOG] So give us the lowdown
on this "Woodpecker."
He got game or
is he just scenery?
[TAMAKI]
Now, now.
That's for all of us
to discover together.
[PURPLE SKULL]
One of these days, I swear...
[PIGTAILS]
You always say that!
[SNAKE] Stingy S.O.B.
[TAMAKI] Ah.
Excuse me for a moment.
What is it?
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4A] I know
you're with clients, sir...
But we've got a
situation in G block.
Crow seems to have
gone on the warpath.
[CRASHING SOUND]
Oh, man... Like he's
slicing a damn pizza...
Is that who we saw
in the courtyard?
[SENJI]
So Woodpecker...
Is all this just like a
warm up for you or what...?
'Cause that's fine but...
If you wanted something
a little more serious,
I'm up for that, too.
I dunno, in this light
it doesn't look like
he's the same dude.
Hey... How long are you
planning on staring me down?
[GANTA GASPS]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
Heh...
[THUD]
[GANTA YELLS]
[SLICING SOUND]
[CLATTERING]
[GANTA]
He-He's gonna kill me...
No...
[SENJI]
C'mon... Are you serious?
You're... the
Woodpecker, right?
[GANTA] The what?
The psycho who slaughtered
his class in Nagano...
The fuck you mean "what?"
You holding out
on me for a reason...?
Or you just gonna
bleed to death?
Bleed...?
[GANTA THINKING]
I can use that again...?
Like... Like earlier...
And all I've got
to do... is bleed.
[GANTA GRUNTS]
All I've got to do...
[SENJI]
Goddamn it...
I guess you're not as
advertised, huh...?
Sucks, I was really
looking forward to this.
But you're just another
boring little shit.
Stop right there.
[SENJI GASPS]
For all of my friends...
For Mimi and Yamakatsu...
And for all of the torture
you've put me through!
[SENJI YELLS]
[SENJI GRUNTS]
Ahhhhhhhh...!
[GANTA GASPS]
Oh no...
[SENJI LAUGHS]
Wait...
What the hell did he
just try to do...?
And... how the hell
did it not work?!
[SENJI LAUGHS]
Excellent shot, kid...
Dead center...
Not sure why you bring
your friends into it...
But hey, it's
an effective tac...
Let's see some more of it!
Huh...?
How can you not know?
[SENJI LAUGHS]
[GANTA GASPS]
[GANTA THINKING]
Hold on.
[RED MAN] Kishi!
He's not the Red Man... Is he?
[SENJI] 'Kay, I'm waiting for
you to start making sense.
[GANTA] I don't...
I don't understand.
That power.
My friends...
Wait a second, are you talking
about the kids you butchered?
Screw that...
that's your bed.
It wasn't me!
Those people were my friends!
I didn't kill them!
But I saw who did...
And he could do what you do.
[SENJI SIGHS]
Get this straight...
The name is Senji.
Whoever you're talking about,
I ain't your man...
There's more'n a few
people can do what we do.
[GANTA] Huh?
[SENJI]
Gimme a break...
You really think you
and the guy you're trying
to pin your crimes on
are the only Deadmen
in the world?
[GANTA]
What's... Deadmen?
[SENJI] Come on, genius.
It's in the name of this place.
Use your damn head...
You imagine they keep
G-block all tucked away
just for the hell of it?
Seriously?
Heh...
Man, you are in the dark.
[SENJI]
Only batshit crazies
think they're
special, you know...
Well, batshit crazies...
and idiot kids...
Well then... Let's see.
Which are you?
[SHIRO GASPS]
Show me what you're
made of Woodpecker!
C'mon, give it to me!
[SHIRO YELLS]
[THUD]
[SENJI GASPS]
You stop picking on Ganta!
[SENJI SCREAMS]
You... You're
a girl... Oh god!
[SHIRO]
Lay... off... my... friend...
...or... answer... to... me!
[SENJI]
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Just, just pull this over
yourself, please...
How come?
What do you mean?!
'Cause the outfit
you're in right now...
...leaves nothing
to the imagination!
[YOH]
Dude, what's wrong with you?
[SHIRO YELLS]
Don't do that!
Promise you'll
leave Ganta alone!
Your bouncing is making
me uncomfortable.
[GANTA THINKING] So he...
He's really not the Red Man.
[GUNSHOTS]
[SENJI GRUNTS]
Huh...?
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[SHIRO] Ganta?
You... bastards...
We were just warming up.
[THUD]
Ganta...? Ganta...!
[SHIRO GRUNTS ANGRILY]
Shiro, no!
[SHIRO YELLS]
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B YELLS]
[BEEPING]
[SHIRO YELLS]
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4A] The situation
has been contained, sir...
G-block is clean.
[TAMAKI]
Excellent...
So I take it that
nine-six-oh-one
is in good shape...?
Not too roughed up?
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4A]
Well...
Dear oh dear...
Not making any new
friends today, I see.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
Oh, no rest for the wicked, sir.
Come on, wiggle worm.
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4A]
Uh, Promoter, sir...
One of them doesn't have
an identification code.
Really...? That's odd.
It must be
a server error...
Makina won't be
pleased to hear that.
No, indeed.
[MAKINA]
Not a damn thing?
[GUARD 3E] No ma'am.
It's like Necro Macro
just disappeared...
And on top of that,
there's absolutely zero
trace of the prisoners.
[MAKINA GRUNTS ANGRILY]
That double-crossing
son of a bitch...
He's doing this
to piss me off.
Uh, ma'am...?
Where are you running off to?
[MAKINA]
To see the Director.
[KASUGA GASPS]
Really...? But I thought
Tamaki had to approve--
[MAKINA] Tamaki can kiss
my ass right about now.
I'm not rolling
over on this.
Protocol be damned...
I will have some answers.
Meanies... What have
you done with Ganta?!
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
I told you,
we're on the way to see him.
Stop being such a pain.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B] Damn it...
Like we don't already have our
hands full with that bunch...
Hey...
What makes G-block
so damn special
that you've got
to hide it away?
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B] Really?
You haven't figured that out?
'Cause these people
are dangerous, kid...
They're infected
with branch of sin.
Can't let 'em mix
with the gen. pop.
Infected...? Well, shit...
What kind of disease
is "branch of sin?"
[G-BLOCK GUARDS] Uhh...
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
You think they give grunts
like us the details?
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B]
Yeah... how should we know?
[BEEPING]
[YOH THINKING]
Deadmen...? Branch of sin?
It's a "Wonderland"...
No doubt about that.
[DOOR OPENS]
[THUDDING]
[SHIRO GRUNTS]
Hey! Where's Ganta?!
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
What am I, your valet?
Find him yourself.
Just don't
come back here.
Don't even talk
about "here."
Ah... These'll cover
our handling fee.
Hell no...!
I earned those cast points!
Give 'em back!
[SMACK]
[THUD]
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
See ya later.
You meanies!
I don't like this...
[GANTA GRUNTS]
What's going on...?! Hey...!
Not cool...! Ugh!
[TAMAKI]
It'd help if you stayed still.
The equipment prefers
that you not struggle...
The data flow, you understand.
You're... my lawyer...
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
[TAKASHIMA EXHALES]
[TAKASHIMA]
Unbelievable...
You couldn't hold off
for one more day?
Shut up...
Oh dear...
Someone's blushing.
Whatever...
[FOOTSTEPS]
Hey... Don't come near me.
[TAKASHIMA]
I have to check for fever.
Ugh... Look, it's probably
just the anesthesia...
Ugh...! Doc!
Put on some clothes!
What...?
Oh for crying out loud,
I'm dressed like a professional.
Build up an immunity already.
Yeah, and how 'bout you
build up a freakin' wardrobe?!
[TAKASHIMA]
You poor thing...
A couple of ribs
and your sternum...
Huh. Pretty clean break.
Heh...
The kid hit me dead center...
I like him.
Well, you're in
no shape to fight
and you won't
be for a while.
I'll recommend
to the Promoter
that he either
postpone or cancel.
[SENJI LAUGHS]
[TAKASHIMA GASPS]
[CLATTERING]
Don't even try...
This is my fight...
You understand?
Who gives a shit about
a couple of ribs?
I don't break.
[TAMAKI]
Your trial... Ah!
Those were good times.
Purely supplementary
for me, though.
My real work is in
promotions, you see.
What are you
talking about?
[TAMAKI] I have to be a Jack of
All Trades in order to secure,
shall we say, the
"necessary talent."
Your case wasn't
my first... or my last.
[GANTA GASPS]
That video... You...
[TAMAKI] Hmm?
Oh, yes... I know
a gifted impersonator...
Setting it up couldn't
have been easier...
Getting the footage out there...
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
...that was the thorny bit.
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[TAMAKI] Fortunately everything
dovetailed splendidly,
allowing us to focus on more--
Shut, up! You asshole...!
How can you joke about this?!
Son of a bitch...!
Get me off this goddamn thing!
I'm not a fucking animal!
Bastard!
I'm going to kill you!
[GANTA GRUNTS]
I'll make you regret this.
[TAMAKI]
So feisty. Heh...
Let's reign you in.
[ELECTRIC BUZZING]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
Let's begin by
polishing your manners.
See... I... Well,
I'm rather... old school.
"Sir..." "Ma'am..."
"Why, thank you..."
[SCIENTIST 3A]
Please, sir!
You mustn't put so much
strain on the boy!
It might aversely
affect tomorrow's test...
[SYSTEM POWERS DOWN]
[GANTA BREATHES HEAVILY]
We wouldn't want
that... Would we?
[TAMAKI] I see... tomorrow
is your first time battling...
We're expecting
a marvelous show.
Oh and trust me...
It will be very special.
The Woodpecker...
versus the Crow...
Who I believe you've
already met... Heh...
[TAMAKI SNAPS]
I look forward to seeing
you at full bore, Deadman.
No way...! I won't do it!
[TAMAKI] These little tests
are the reality of G-block...
And... if you win, the prize
is not only free candy,
but an obscene
amount of cast points.
So stay positive.
Why don't you take your
prizes and cram 'em up your ass?
[TAMAKI] Now, now...
You'll want to save up
that aggression for
the ring, birdie.
Emerge victorious from
enough of our tests
and you'll get to
meet your nemesis.
[GANTA]
What is that supposed to mean?
Please... What do
you think it means?
The man you saw
massacre your class...
Surely you'd relish
the chance to face him...?
Of course, I suspect he finds
the prospect just as compelling.
He must have left you
alive for a reason, after all.
Quite portentous when a creature
like that takes a shine to one,
don't you think?
Incidentally, your name for
him--Red Man... very nice...
We know him by the somewhat
less flattering moniker...
..."Wretched Egg."
He's the nucleus of what we do;
the source of our Deadman
supply, you might say.
Of course... I knew it...
He's, here...
He's behind this.
Show me the bastard!
I'll kill him! I swear I will!
When I get out of here
I'm gonna kill all of you!
[TAMAKI]
Heh... First things first.
Impress us during
tomorrow's Carnival Corpse
and we'll discuss it.
[GANTA] What do you
mean... "Carnival Corpse"?
[TAMAKI] Oh, it's to
die for, believe you me.
[GANTA GRUNTS FEARFULLY]
[TAMAKI SNAPS]
[TAMAKI]
Watch and learn, son.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] Carnival
Corpse, boys and girls...!
The bloodiest,
awesom-est attraction
in the whole
carrion-coated park...!
Remember the "Red Hole" debacle
in Tokyo ten years ago?
Well, some of the lucky
so-and-so's who lived through it
got infected with Branch
of Sin for their trouble.
We call 'em Deadmen,
and let me tell you,
their powers are gruesome
beyond your wildest dreams!
If you're clamoring for
carnage, giddy for gore,
bug-eyed for blood and guts,
you haven't lived till
you've seen a pair of these
incredible freaks go
head-to-head to the death!
[UNFORTUNATE GIRL 4A SCREAMS]
[UNFORTUNATE MAN 4A YELLS]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
Quite rad,
wouldn't you agree?
Of course
you would...
Let's go over
it again, eh?
[GANTA]
No! No! Noooooo!
[BEEPING]
[SENJI GRUNTS]
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4D] Hey. I've got
your latest issue of "Mastery."
[SENJI]
Toss it over there.
[SENJI GRUNTS]
Woodpecker... You better
not be just some fluke...
...'cause I ain't... Trust me.
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA] When you're
pitted against someone
farther down the
rabbit hole than you,
dim memories of life before
the fall just won't cut it.
The cage is open;
hope has flown,
and in its place: you,
right before the
door slams shut.