[CICADAS CHIRP]
[PHONE LADY]
Boy or girl, young or old...
Here, everyone's wildest
dreams roam free.
That's the magic, the thrill...
of Deadman Wonderland!
[MIMI]
Morning, Ganta.
[GANTA] Huh...?
Oh hey, Mimi.
Breakfast in class again, huh?
Where's your shadow?
No idea.
Whatcha lookin' at anyway?
Oh...
I was just kinda digging
some stuff up online
about the whole
prison-tour field trip thing.
Oh yeah...? Are you as
stoked about it as I am?
I mean, the place
is supposed to be
tricked out like
an amusement park!
[GANTA] I know...
Just cheap they're not
taking us somewhere farther.
But Tokyo's nostalgic...
Don't you think so?
If you say so, I guess...
It's been ten years
since I was there...
I don't really remember much.
[YAMAKATSU]
He's got a point...
We were all kids...
The place could be totally
different and we'd never know.
Hey Yamakatsu,
what's up?
Thanks a lot for skippin'
out on me, doofus.
It's not my fault if someone
sleeps like a freakin' log.
You're killing me...
Yesterday the shoe was
on the other foot.
How far you gonna take this?
[GANTA]
There wouldn't be a shoe
if the genius hadn't
lost my save data.
[YAMAKATSU] You weren't
even past level seven!
Yeah... So...
The fieldtrip, right...?
Great idea... That'll fly.
Lot of folks think "Tokyo,"
they still think the Red Hole.
Not everybody who survived it
has Ganta's knack
for selective memory.
Oh, come on!
Not this crap again!
[MIMI]
Chill out, guys...
Does it matter
where they take us?
Seriously...
We're less than two weeks
out from entrance exams...
The name of the
game is distraction.
Well, I'm down
for it if you are...
Anything to get us
out of here, I guess.
[MIMI] We lived it up at that
lame, old water park last year.
Where we go doesn't matter,
let's just make
the best of it okay?
Sure.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS:
"Westminster Quarters"]
[Instrumental "Lullaby"]
Huh?
That song...
I've heard it before...
I know I have--
How is he...?
We... We're on the third floor!
[YAMAKATSU]
Whoa! What the hell?!
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[STUDENTS SCREAM]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[GANTA] What just happened?
[DRIPPING SOUND]
Is this a... nightmare?
[GANTA] Hey, Mimi. You okay?
[GANTA SCREAMS]
Kishi!
Oh god... Please, no...
[GANTA YELLS]
Would your name
be Ganta Igarashi?
Yeah...
[DETECTIVE 1-A] We have
a few questions for you.
I'm afraid... you'll need
to come with us.
Huh?
[REPORTER LADY 1-A] Reports
indicate that of the thirty
middle school students known
to have been in the classroom
at the time of the killing,
a staggering
twenty-nine were slain.
"...an inside job."
That's what police
are calling it.
And indeed as of
this afternoon
the massacre's sole survivor
has been formally charged.
This... cannot be real.
Court appointed attorney
coming through, gentlemen.
A pleasure.
[GANTA] What...?
No... Listen...
Please, guys...
You have to believe me!
I saw him...!
It's the man in red;
he's the one you want!
[GANTA RETCHES]
Hold on...
I can prove it; he got me.
Huh?!
Where did it go? It was...
Oh, you poor
traumatized child...
You've been through so much.
No one's going to
hurt you anymore, son.
Listen... I didn't do this!
Of course not...
And I'm going to do
everything within my power
to ensure the judges know that.
[JUDGE 1-A] Upon careful
consideration of the evidence...
Unprecedented
though it may be...
...I fear...
...the only recourse
that we have...
...is capital punishment.
[GANTA GASPS]
This isn't real...
It can't be...
I'm a kid...
I'm innocent...
[HANDCUFFS LOCK]
Why is this happening to me?
[GANTA CRIES]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[GANTA] Screw all of you!
What the hell's going on?!
Why won't any of you
people listen to me?!
[GANTA YELLS IN PAIN]
[FATHER 1-A]
Take your fucking hands off me!
[FATHER 1-B]
Kill him! Kill him!
They were my friends,
I wouldn't--
[GANTA GASPS]
Look, I... Mimi was...
Don't you say her name...
Don't you ever say her name!
[PHONE CLATTERS]
[REPORTER LADY 1-A]
...startling new footage.
I'm innocent... I swear it...
[GANTA] 'Course I'm gonna
walk. Think about it.
No one's gonna buy
a middle school kid
being behind something
this horrific...
Who's the lawyer here? Shit...
'Sides, I'm just a baby;
they couldn't throw the book
at me if they wanted to.
Am I right?
Huh... Who in the hell is that?
It didn't really matter
to me who it was...
But it's more fun
carving up people
whose faces you gotta look
at every day... Heh....
'Specially the
stuck-up lil' whores...
I couldn't resist seein'
for myself whether
their cunts were as full
of shit as their assholes.
Know what I mean?
And... You know...
Figured if I'm gonna do any
I might as well do 'em all...
Kinda like passing out handmade
birthday party invitations...
Yeah, yeah.
The weapon... c'mon...
Thought we've been
through this already...
When I hear them say "innocent"
I'll show you
where it's hidden...
Heh... Call it
my god-given right
for being the cleverest
guy in the room.
[GANTA LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[GANTA GASPS]
I treated you like
my flesh and blood
for the better part
of ten years...
I didn't... do this...
I keep telling you...
[MIMI'S FATHER] Why...?
Why did you take
my little girl?!
Listen to me... please...
Let go of me!
I have rights!
The little son of a bitch
owes me an answer!
[TAMAKI]
Sorry about that...
I really should've
been more cautious.
What?
If I'd known someone was
filming the two of us,
I would have tried to
reign in your gloating.
But... but you know
that wasn't me!
Well, there's no
point in our filing
for an appeal now, I suppose...
No judge worth their salt
would ever grant you one.
No, hold on...!
Mr. Tamaki...!
Mr. Tamaki!
Come back!
[GANTA CRIES]
This is a nightmare...
It's got to be.
[GANTA CRIES]
[SHIRO SINGS "Lullaby"]
♪ Naughty birdie's
song is made... ♪
♪ by pecking holes in trees... ♪
♪ Willows, cedars,
sycamores... ♪
♪ and proud oaks
reduced to cheese... ♪
♪ woodland gods,
all in a huff, ♪
♪ have forever cursed
your naughty beak... ♪
♪ what it pecks,
it poisons now; ♪
♪ your food, your nest,
even your young... ♪
♪ your friends now
all fear you... ♪
♪ But your tears ring
clearly through the wood, ♪
♪ even as they
taint the dew... ♪
♪ Such a sad,
sad, little birdy... ♪
♪ Maybe someday this song
will lift the curse ♪
♪ and set you free... ♪
[SHIRO] He's here.
Ganta...
[MAKINA]
Deadman Wonderland...
Built at the epicenter
of the sinkhole
that engulfed Tokyo
a decade ago;
an incident popularly
known as The Red Hole.
Welcome to the first and only
privately owned
corrections facility in Japan,
where inmates pay
their debt to society
by lubricating
the tourist trade.
[FOOTSTEPS]
I am Makina,
the chief warden here.
And you're Ganta
Igarashi, aren't you?
[PRISONER 1-A GASPS]
You look a lot softer than I'd
expect someone like you to...
Don't think sheep's
clothing will charm anyone
into commuting your sentence.
[GANTA THINKING]
I shouldn't be here.
[MAKINA] Unless you've
been living under a rock...
You know how unique
our little operation is.
Administrative autonomy,
boys and girls.
Everything is done in-house.
Hardened capital offenders and
snot-nosed juvenile delinquents
perform under the same roof.
The money this little
institution thrives on
is the money you make us.
Does the fresh meat
have any questions?
[PRISONER 1-B] Uh, yeah...
How big are those titties?
I'm a G.
[PRISONERS] Whoa!
Your knapsacks contain
all the bare necessities.
And if you're clever, you can
survive on them for three days.
Now a word about your collars.
They're not just how we tag,
track, and--if needed--prod you.
They're much more involved.
Once a day--
[GANTA YELLS]
[THUD]
Oh crap, dude...!
I totally didn't
even see you there!
I'm sorry man,
hope I didn't hurt you.
I think I'm okay.
[MAKINA] Hey. Cart boy.
Return the goods and
I won't slice you open.
What...? No... I...
My cart's my
responsibility.
Just remember that
I gave you the choice.
[YOH SCREAMS]
All due respect,
that was overkill.
Get the paramedics
to section A now.
[PRISONER 1-C]
Whoa... Bitch is nuts!
[YOH GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[MAKINA]
I don't disagree.
But get used to it...
This is life, boys.
Your life...
From now until we see
fit to cut you loose.
Or at least...
...until Wonderland
claims you for its own.
You can't just
slice up anybody.
We don't want
the newbies left with
the impression that
this is a free-for-all.
You didn't even go over
death row regulations.
And what would've
been the point?
Five-five-eight-zero
was the only short-timer
in today's bunch...
And his "accident" is
just around the corner.
Unless the decision
has been rescinded?
I... understand.
He's the only
newcomer to death row
out of the batch we received
this afternoon, but...
[MAKINA] The "accident's"
a ridiculous precaution.
He's just a kid.
It isn't like he'll last long.
So what are you so antsy about?
[TAMAKI] Chief Warden,
when you find a
beautifully wrapped present
on, say, your vanity
table, what do you do?
[MAKINA] I open it.
[TAMAKI]
Indeed, as would I.
Wrapping be damned,
I just want to get at
what I know is inside.
[DRILLING SOUNDS]
[GATES CREAK SHUT]
[GANTA BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SPARKS SIZZLE]
[CROWD MAN 1-A] Die!
[CROWD YELLS]
Somebody please just kill me.
[GANTA THINKING] Mimi...
You want me to kill you?
I could do it
in one swing.
[GANTA YELLS]
Or not, if you dodge me...
[GANTA] What?
Silly boy!
[GANTA YELLS]
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
I don't even know who you--
[GANTA YELLS]
Ah ha!
Huh...?
That was a fib back there, huh?
Hey...! You callin' me a liar?!
[SHIRO] Yep... Hear that?
This part wants nothing
to do with being killed.
How the hell would
you know what it wants?
We've never even met.
[SHIRO] Yes we have.
Oh yeah...?
Then how come
I don't remember you?
Like that really matters.
Ganta and Shiro are
the bestest buddies!
Wait a second...
How do you know my name?
If you don't want to
be killed, then cheer up.
What does
that even mean?
'Kay, look...
Last I checked,
buddies don't try to bash
each others' skulls in...
Get me?
So you wouldn't
kill your friends...
[GANTA GASPS]
Of course I wouldn't!
Not on your life!
I'd never intentionally
hurt the people I care about.
Ow!
[PRISONER 1-A]
Do all mass murderers
get the four-star
treatment here?
C'mon... Don't
provoke the kid.
I'm just sayin', ditch-digging
doesn't seem like that
much of a punishment.
[PRISONER 1-B]
I don't know, man...
Kid looks more like somebody's
doormat than a ruthless psycho.
Heh...
Use your damn head...
If he looked like what he is,
he wouldn't have been able
to ice so many people.
Don't get any ideas about your
reputation meaning jack shit
in these parts, schizoid.
Hey... Bet you got a hard-on
when they passed
your sentence...
Just like when you smeared
your little friends' guts
all over the wall.
[GANTA THINKING]
It wasn't me... It wasn't me...
Did you do it because
you were picked on?
Did all the popular
chicks ignore you?
C'mon, your secret's
safe with me...
What was it like
killing those kids--
[PRISONER 1-A YELLS]
You're a big meanie!
Ganta would never intentionally
hurt the people he cares about.
You... bitch!
[PRISONER 1-A YELLS]
Woah!
[THUD]
[PRISONER 1-B YELLS]
What in the hell
is her damage?
I thought all the A Block
gimps were on ditch detail.
[GANTA] You bastard!
[GANTA YELLS]
[PRISONER 1-A] This ain't
a classroom, you little shit.
[GANTA YELLS]
[TAMAKI]
The "man in red" he says...
Few people witness
the Wretched Egg in action
and live to tell about it...
You're extremely fortunate.
Unless you're not.
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
There are two choices
before you right now, boy...
Get kicked into
the dirt and perish...
...or become my
shiny new plaything.
[GANTA] Stop!
You're hurting me!
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[GANTA THINKING]
Please... Not like this.
[BEEP]
[EXPLOSION]
[METAL CREAKS AND SNAPS]
[GANTA THINKING]
I don't want to die in here.
I want to clear my name.
And him...
I want him to pay for
what he's done to me;
for what he's done
to my friends...
For what he did to Mimi!
I want to live.
I want to live!
[WHOOSHING SOUND]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[ANNOUNCER MAN]
We have a death row inmate
resisting execution in area D4.
A hostage has been taken.
Immediate backup requested.
[PRISONER 1-D GROANS]
[KASUGA] If you know
what's good for you,
you'll let him
go right now!
Shut your hole!
I need some candy!
Bring me some candy or
I'll slit his throat right now!
Ma'am, the prisioner refusing
to lay down his weapon!
And has the data on
his collar been confirmed?
No ma'am.
Keep him occupied
with small talk...
He doesn't
have too long.
Yes ma'am!
Uh... Hey...
So... All
things considered,
it sure is
a nice day out.
Damn it...!
Please... help me!
I don't have any more
cast points left!
I'm begging you...
I need candy...
[RAPID BEEPING]
[PRISONER 1-D YELLS]
[COLLAR RELEASES]
I'm sorry, but the
rules are the rules.
[BEEPING]
[PARK ANNOUNCER LADY]
Thank you for visiting
Deadman Wonderland.
Come back and
see us again soon.
I'm not dead...?
Holy crap... How am
I not dead after that?
Oh no...!
How bad are you hurt?!
Wowie... I am so full.
Wake up!
Hey you.
Did I say full, 'cause
if it's snack time again...
Will you answer me?!
Are you hurt?
Oh hey!
I've got an idea!
Next time let's eat
our snacks together!
Huh?
Snack time is so much more fun
when you have someone
sweet to share it with.
Yeah sure...
I guess you've got to have
fun whenever you can...
Yup...!
Bestest buddies
forever and ever!
[PARK ANNOUNCER LADY]
Welcome, one and all,
to Deadman Wonderland!
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA]
Death row inmates must
consume candy once
every three days.
To secure their portion,
they're required to make
a spectacle of themselves,
risking death virtually
every step of the way...
Life's a bitch.