[OFFICIAL 3-A]
Does the word "restraint"
mean anything to you?
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
[TAMAKI]
Yesterday was a work of art.
It's not my fault the sheep
can't see beyond their blinders.
Can I help it
if I'm a visionary?
[OFFICIAL 3-B] You've gone
way too far this time!
How many corpses did you
rack up at that damn race?
Some of them weren't
even on death row!
[OFFICIAL 3-C]
That was a public execution!
Our protections
only extend so far!
[OFFICIAL 3-A] We should
meet with the director!
This child wastes our time!
[TAMAKI] Ha! You all know
who really runs this place...
...and Daddy's too busy
fending off the grim reaper.
So... Shouldn't you be trotting
out your "Oliver Twist" shtick
to the government?
[OFFICIALS GRUMBLE]
After all, keeping your dirty
little secret tucked away
safely in our humble abode
doesn't come cheaply.
♪ opening song ♪
[SHIRO]
That was so tasty!
Didja like it?
Yeah... It really
hit the spot.
Then we should eat our
snacks together all the time.
'kay...
[SHIRO GIGGLES]
Goodbye, my bestest friend!
[GANTA THINKING]
There's just one problem...
Today... Today's the day I die.
[BEEP]
[PRISONER 3-C]
That race was a bloodbath.
What the hell, man?!
Betcha those clean-up guys
racked up some killer overtime.
Yeah, and even if people
wanted to quit halfway through,
too bad, so sad.
[PRISONER 3-C]
They smoke all those dudes,
and nobody even wins?
I don't get it.
[PRISONER 3-B] I'm just
glad I sat it out, y'know?
[YOH THINKING] No kidding.
That race was impossible.
How the hell did
they reach the end?
If I had entered,
I'd be a corpse right now.
It's gotta be the new kid.
I just know it...
They cranked up
the danger 'cause of him.
[GANTA INTERNALLY]
"Dear Mimi's father,
I was gonna write a will,
but I don't have anything.
Or anyone. Not anymore.
I know you don't believe
me that I'm innocent.
I know you think
I killed Mimi...
...and Yamakatsu and
all the other kids...
But I didn't.
And today... I'm going
to be executed for it."
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[PAPER TEARS]
Dammit...! I wanna live!
No way...
They stuck you in
here with my dumb ass?
Well it looks like we're
gonna be roommates...
What're the odds, huh?
Yoh, I thought...
[YOH]
Got something for you...
Trust me, you're gonna want it.
[GANTA]
Is that candy candy?
[YOH] If I hadn't
been such a klutz,
you wouldn't have lost
yours in the first place.
I wanted to
make it up you.
Seriously, man.
You need it.
So here...
Just take it.
Yeah...?
Are you sure?
Absolutely!
All right...
Three more days...
Thank you so much, Yoh!
I'm totally in
your debt forever!
[YOH] Heh...
[YOH THINKING]
Not like I had a choice...
Damn near got cut
in half to make it happen.
I just don't get it...
Why's the promoter got such
a friggin' hard-on for you?
There's a new prisoner coming
in today who interests me.
You think you can
keep an eye out?
Report everything back to me,
no matter how trivial...
And in return...
Do you have any questions?
Who cares as long as
there's cast points in it.
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
You are the model
inmate, my dear boy.
[YOH THINKING]
Whatever he's in for...
...it's gotta beat being dead.
[GANTA CHOKES]
Are you okay?
I know it tastes
like crap, but damn...
I know...!
Let's go chase it down
with something tasty.
[PHONE RINGS]
[TAMAKI]
Yeah...? Make it snappy.
The whole Mother Goose
System is off-line?
You're saying...
it has flown the coop?
[SCIENTIST 3-A]
I'm so sorry, sir...
We had an unknown
error pop up during
a routine
maintenance check,
and before we knew
it, the system--
[TAMAKI] Quit babbling
and fix the goddamn thing!
Yes sir!
If the Egg begins to
laugh again we're done for.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[RED MAN HISSES]
[GANTA]
But... I'm completely broke.
[YOH] Nah, this time
it's my treat, man;
From one
cellmate to another.
Dude, you're awesome!
[YOH THINKING]
I don't get it...
This kid really fucked
up a whole classroom?
There's no way...
He seems so vanilla.
[GANTA] Huh...
[YOH] You there?
[GANTA] Ah! Sorry...
Just kinda thinking about
the last time I had ice cream.
[GANTA THINKING]
Man, what I wouldn't give
to live that afternoon again...
[CLOCK TICKING]
[BELL RINGS]
[GANTA YELLS]
[YOH]
Oh shit, are you okay?!
Dude...! Talk to me!
[GANTA YELLS]
That... that's the Red Man!
You... son of a...!
[WHOOSHING]
[PRISONERS YELL]
[PRISONER 3-H] My hand!
[PRISONERS YELL FEARFULLY]
Is it a bomb... a hurricane?
No...! What in the hell
is going on here...?!
[GANTA YELLS]
[YOH YELLS]
[GANTA GASPS]
[GANTA THINKING] Why...?!
Yoh and Shiro...!
You're not gonna
murder them, too!
[GANTA YELLS]
[WHOOSH]
He's summoning his Branch!
[GANTA]
I hate you...!
I'll hate you...
as long as I live!
Go rot in helllllll!
[EXPLOSION]
What... the hell?!
Did he just blast something
outta his hand?!
[RED MAN LAUGHS]
[GANTA] Don't run away
from me, you coward!
Come back!
[GANTA YELLS]
[GANTA]
You... bas...
[SCIENTIST 3-A] The Mother
Goose System is back online!
We've locked onto the
Wretched Egg's wavelength!
[SCIENTIST 3-B] Confirmed.
Deploying capture team!
Great...! This was
no mere coincidence!
This is the christening
of a brand new member!
[YOH]
It smells like blood...
"Just watch the new kid," huh?
Well to hell with that shit!
This is way too crazy for me!
Floating monsters
in red armor...
...and a cellmate who's
a fucking freak...?!
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
Welcome... to
the grand abattoir!
This is the true face
of Deadman Wonderland!
[GANTA YELLS]
[CLATTERING]
[SHIRO] Oops...
[SHIRO] So I kinda ate all your
snacks while you were asleep,
and I feel really bad about it.
A dream?
Guess not.
They said terrorists
attacked in the courtyard...
What is
a terrorist?
[GANTA THINKING]
I remember we were eating...
...and my chest started
to hurt real bad...
And then that blood thing...!
I threw it...
at the Red Man!
What the hell was he
doing in the courtyard?!
And how did I
even manage that...?
Red Man...?
What're those?
There's no cut...
so then... how...?
[GANTA THINKING]
It happened before, remember?
Something happened
to me... But what?
[PRISONER 3-E]
I saw it too.
[GANTA AND SHIRO] Huh...?
He was wearing those
freaky red restraints!
It's gotta be the guy.
You know... that's my
second time seein' him...
He burst through a wall...
Couple years back...
Just blew through it
like it was paper.
Same MO, with
that crazy whirlwind.
Rumor has it they got the guy
in permanent solitary
lock down in G Block,
wherever that is...
[SHIRO]
What's the matter, buddy?
G Block, huh?
[GANTA THINKING]
Watch your back, Red Man...!
I know where you're hiding...
And as soon as I find it...
I'm coming for you.
[SENJI]
Dead center!
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
[GUARD 3-A]
Yes, ma'am.
The attack earlier
was reported as
a terrorist bombing by
a radical human rights group.
[MAKINA]
And the truth?
[GUARD 3-A] Well...
according to Mr. Tamaki,
the case is closed.
[MAKINA]
I don't know what
that frothing hyena's
got his teeth into...
...but I have a damn good hunch
this inmate is likely
at the crux of it.
[KASUGA]
Five-five-eight-zero?
He's just a kid.
True... but looks
can be deceiving.
It seems this kid has
gotten his hands on some
high-tech weaponry somehow.
But, Chief
Warden Makina...
Isn't that...?
Yes...
It's impossible.
[GUARDS GASP]
That's of course, unless...
...it's the boy himself
who's the high-tech weaponry.
[KASUGA GASPS]
Order is the bedrock
of any corrections facility
and that goes triple
for Deadman Wonderland.
If I have to break a few eggs
to maintain that order,
then so be it.
I'm ordering an All Red.
I want the kid in chains
within the hour.
Do I make myself clear?!
Yes, ma'am!
She's so cool!
Uh... but
Chief Warden...
You're not really going
to let it out again, are you?
[MAKINA] Why do I issue
emergency orders as codes?
Ma'am...!
Codes serve to
minimize response time
by substituting for
lengthy explanations!
[MAKINA]
There you have it.
[GUARD 3-A AND GUARD 3-B]
Right!
This prison is
going into lockdown!
Necro Macro lockdown release...!
Authorization
sequence code is:
Two, Two, Three,
Delta, Oscar, Delta...!
Seven, seven, eight, five!
[POWERING UP]
[SPARKS]
[HEAVY THUD]
[MAKINA]
We used it against
a rampaging prisoner
four years ago.
It took him out,
along with 24 others...
The project's been in
mothballs ever since.
So that means...
...you think the boy's
gonna kill enough people
to make using it...
...the lesser
evil, yes.
[KASUGA OVER INTERCOM]
Attention.
The prison is being
placed on lockdown.
All prisoners and staff
must return to their cells
or quarters immediately
and remain there
until further notice.
Also, Inmate 5580
is to report in at once!
[TAMAKI] Leave it to Makina to
blow things out of proportion...
But what about you?
Are you fine with
the prospect of Ganta
becoming damaged goods
on your watch, Yoh?
How am I supposed to
babysit a freakin' monster?
And what in the hell
are those guys, anyway?!
[TAMAKI SIGHS]
Do calm down...
We've already captured the
floating one in the red cape.
You see, young
master Ganta...
...is now a guest of the
real Deadman Wonderland.
I'd prefer that
he not die today.
[YOH THINKING]
"Real," huh?
[TAMAKI] Lose the goose...
and no more golden eggs.
[KASUGA OVER INTERCOM] Inmate
5580 is to report in at once!
Once again, Inmate 5580
is to report in at once!
Inmate 5580,
that's me, isn't it?
Why are they calling me?
Ganta, wait up!
What's going on?
Why are
we running?
There isn't time to explain!
Oh, I get it now!
We're having
a race, huh?
[GANTA]
No, wait...!
[DOORS SLAM SHUT]
[POUNDING]
[GANTA]
C'mon! What the hell?!
[YOH] Welcome to Deadman
Wonderland on lockdown.
[GANTA] Huh...?
Yoh, what're you--
Listen to me.
If you don't report in
as soon as possible,
well, you saw what
happened to me.
[YOH THINKING] Just do it... I'm
not in the mood for this crap!
Sorry... I can't.
Well, not yet, at least.
We're in the
middle of a race!
Huh?
[GANTA]
No, we're not!
I know you saw him, Yoh.
You saw the Red Man...
He's the sick bastard who did
what I've been put away for.
He murdered all
of my friends...
Everybody that I
ever cared about!
All of 'em?
[YOH] Wait... so he broke out,
went on a killing spree,
and came back?
That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard!
Look, I heard they keep him
hidden away in G Block...
So that's
where I'm going...
To find the Red Man.
G Block...?
But there's
no such place.
Huh?!
[YOH]
Check the map... See...?
This place is split into
six blocks, A through F.
There's no place a
G block could even fit.
No way...
Now look, man...
You really oughta check in
with the guards before they--
G Block?
[GANTA] Huh?
If that's the place
I think you're talking about,
then I know how to get there.
Well, what are we waiting for?!
[SHIRO] Maybe I
don't feel like it.
Huh?!
Why're you getting all pouty?
If you know,
then just spit it out!
[SHIRO] Don't wanna.
What is it?!
[WHISPERING]
Wait... Just be quiet.
[WHIRRING]
[GANTA, SHIRO, AND YOH GASP]
No! Get it off!
It's one of the
crowd-control robots!
And it's locking
onto target!
Shiro!
Get us outta here!
You're a butthead.
[GANTA SCREAMS]
What's gotten
into you, huh?!
Shiro, c'mon!
Shiro!
Okay... I guess
if I gotta...
[SHIRO YELLS]
[CLATTERING]
All you have to do is nudge
the grate outta the way
and you can go anywhere!
That's... a nudge?
It looks like we've found
the target, ma'am.
We're currently pursuing
5580 and 9061!
He's in cahoots with
that little thief?
Take 'em both out!
Oh crap!
Pull me up... quick!
[EXPLOSION]
[SHIRO AND YOH YELL]
[COUGHING]
[YOH] You're kidding me!
It's trying to kill us...?!
That's messed up...
even for this freak show!
[METAL CREAKS]
[CRASHING]
[GANTA YELLS FEARFULLY]
[SHIRO] Over here!
This way! C'mon!
[GANTA YELLS]
[SPARKING]
[SPARKING AND WHIRRING]
It... it shut down...?
How the hell did
you do that, Yoh?!
I guess you could say
I've got sticky fingers.
[GANTA] Sticky how?
Never mind... Come on,
let's get outta here!
[BUZZING]
[BEEPING]
Why are you so mad...
all of a sudden?
[GANTA GASPS]
G Block... It is real.
[GANTA THINKING]
This is it...
This is where I'll
find the Red Man.
[METAL CREAKS]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[YOH YELLS]
[GANTA YELLS]
[MULTIPLE EXPLOSIONS]
[RATTLING]
[SENJI LAUGHS]
We seem to have
lost track of his signal.
And there isn't any sign of
Necro Macro either, ma'am!
So we lost
both of them?
Inmates don't just disappear
into thin air, dammit!
If those two little punks
have gone off the grid...
...then there's a secret area.
Another portion of
Deadman Wonderland
over which I have
no control...!
Tamaki, you bastard...!
I was so close!
Shiro... Yoh...!
I'm so sorry I dragged
you down here with me!
This has nothing
to do with you!
[YOH THINKING] Oh yeah, a lot of
fucking good that does us now!
[SHIRO]
Duuuummy!
[CRASHING]
You are a big stupid-head!
She just kicked
a damn robot...
That chick has
got mad moves!
[SHIRO]
You're a meanie...!
Whaddya mean it's got nothing
to do with me, Ganta?!
You said he murdered
all of your friends...!
And yeah... I ate your snacks
while you were sleeping, but...!
But it doesn't mean
I don't get to be your friend!
So that's what she was
acting all pissy about...?
Look, he gets it,
just come on down!
You'll be safer on
the ground, okay?!
[GANTA THINKING] She really
means it, doesn't she?
I'm a great friend, Ganta!
[GANTA THINKING]
I do have a friend. Two of 'em.
You're right... I'm sorry.
[LOUD THUD]
[BEEPING AND WHIRRING]
Oh no...! Leave her
alone, you piece of junk!
[GANTA YELLS]
[SHIRO GASPS]
[GANTA THINKING]
Wait a minute...
That attack...!
I can use it to save her!
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[GANTA] Come on...!
Come out already...!
Why aren't you working?!
That robot's gonna kill her!
Shirooooo!
[SLICING]
[EXPLOSION]
[SHIRO YELLS]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[GANTA GASPS]
Heh...
Dead center.
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA]
The sin forms a branch...
...and you're about to meet
another bird who clings to it.
You'd better toughen up
that beak, woodpecker.
You'll need it.
Squawk all you like.
There's no escape to be had
from this blood-spattered cage.