[LAB WORKERS CHATTER]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
♪ opening song ♪
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
Uhh... I'm parched.
God, I hate pullin' shifts
during Carnival Corpse.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B] That
Woodpecker's got spunk, though.
Am I right?
Oh... hold on.
I got you covered...
Can't say this gig
doesn't have perks.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C]
Yeah; thank you, no.
Pretty sure the
brass'd frown on you
confiscating those
from a normal.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B]
Like there's enough on these
for anything but crap.
[MACHINE BEEPS]
[BOTH GUARDS] Uhh...
Huh?!
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B]
Okay. Please please please
tell me I'm not seein' this...
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4C] I see it,
I just don't believe it!
[G-BLOCK GUARD 4B] How in the
hell does some douchey kid
with bangs like a shih tzu
rack up so much cast?!
Ah, damn it...
How hard's it gotta be to
find your way out of here?
Crap!
You didn't see anything.
It's none of your business.
Forget it... It has nothing
to do with why you're here.
Minatsuki...
[GANTA THINKING]
I'm in hell... I have to be.
I thought it was
a nightmare before...
But at least in
gen. pop. I had...
...well, friends.
I hope they're safe...
I really hope they're safe.
[MINATSUKI]
I'm sorry! Please stop!
[MASU]
Aw, no fair! How come?!
[MINATSUKI]
No, Mr. Matsu! Bad!
[MASU]
Pretty please?!
[MINATSUKI]
Yes, I understand that
they look very tasty,
but you can't!
I... I need them for my--
But... My tummy is so empty!
I just can't stand it anymore!
[GANTA] Hey...!
What about this?
Here, be my guest.
Food... for me?!
Wow... Thank you.
Uh, sure.
[CHOMPING]
[MASU]
More... More noms please!
Woah...!
[MASU]
My tummy...
My tummy needs more...!
[GANTA] Whoa!
I'm guessin'
this is your room.
Yes, it is!
It was the closest place I could
think of for us to run. Sorry.
No, this is perfect.
Thanks for saving my
babies from Mr. Matsu.
Uh... Your... name is
Ganta Igarashi, right?
Wait, how...
Oh, so you must have watched
yesterday's Carnival Corpse.
I haven't introduced myself,
my name's Minatsuki...
Oh...! Sit! Please.
I mean, if you want.
[GANTA]
Sure. Thanks.
[MINATSUKI]
I feel terrible.
You'll have to go hungry
now because of me.
What...?
Oh. That...
I haven't had much
of an appetite lately.
Yeah, well after
their first show...
...most people don't.
[GANTA] Yeah...
This place is
really messed up.
Who does stuff like this?
[MINATSUKI]
I know, I... I agree...
Making us hurt complete
and total strangers...
...just to
showcase our powers.
It's all so horrible...
And what it's doing to us...
I can't take it...
I want to die!
[GANTA GASPS]
Aw, cut it out...
That's not...
Uh... So hey...
That smell...
[GANTA STAMMERS]
No...! Uh,
I mean your flowers!
You like them?
This particular kind
is called a primrose.
And of all the flowers in the
world, they're my favorite.
They respond well to
being treated delicately.
Whoa...! Wha...?
[MINATSUKI] My father
didn't really think of me
as a primrose, I'm afraid.
And when I was little, my mom
was killed in the Red Hole.
My dad drank... and sometimes
he'd lose his temper.
I usually just put up
with it, you know...?
But there was this one time,
I thought he was
really going to kill me.
I snapped... Like my
powers suddenly made sense.
My older brother never knew
that I was responsible.
He was convinced the
system railroaded me.
Who'd suspect a sweet little
high school girl could tear
her own father to shreds
with her bare hands... right?
My brother's a nice guy.
He always
treated me delicately.
And here all I can
do is hurt people...
It's not...
It's not your fault.
I hate it... I hate
using this stupid power.
I... hate being part
of the Carnival...
I hate being a
monster...! I...!
[GANTA YELLS]
Oh my god,
I'm so sorry!
[GANTA] Let's run.
What?
Let's do it.
Let's break the hell out.
Just like that?
Think about it.
Can we protect
ourselves or can't we?
You mean...
We could use our...
Oh... I'm sorry...
Look, it's alright.
You don't have to
use your Branch of Sin.
Then how can we...?
I can protect
you with mine.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 6A]
What?! How the hell am I...?
Stupid bitch, they're
called chopsticks...
[G-BLOCK GUARD 6A YELLS]
[MINATSUKI GRUNTS]
[GANTA]
You okay?
I don't think I can
go through with this.
[RUMBLING]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[MINATSUKI] Ganta!
Oh my god, oh my god,
oh my god, I'm sorry...!
It's all my fault!
I am such a klutz!
[G-BLOCK GUARD 6B]
Hey! What's going on?!
Where's your escort?!
Huh...? How 'bout that...
We got ourselves a Woodpecker
and a Hummingbird...
Save those hormones
for the match, kiddos.
[GANTA] Wait, what...?
Hummingbird?
Oh no...
I thought you already
knew about tomorrow.
Huh?
[MINATSUKI]
Tomorrow's Carnival Corpse...
I'm the Hummingbird...
We're supposed to fight.
I thought you knew...
I'm so sorry.
[DIRECTOR] You swish in
here with your line-up...
As though I'm not chin deep in
the dregs of your incompetence
as it is... you imbecile.
Wonderland isn't
your personal abattoir...
Merely a birdcage...
One that I created myself.
Oh... So sorry...
You're plying me with
wisdom again, aren't you?
Ah! But the show
must go on...! Yes?
As if I weren't
already chin deep
in the dregs of
your petty goals.
Bah, you're excited...
Come on you old sour puss...
For one, it's our boy Ganta...
Against the tart, no less.
I mean, please... You and I
are both hot-blooded mammals.
Nothing like a
girlie with teeth
to pull you from
6 to midnight.
Om-nom...! Now that's wit.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
I hope you're ready for
another heapin' helping of
Deadman Wonderland's
balls to the wall blood-fest,
Carnival Corpse!
Now, at first glance,
today's competitors
might appear to be
cruelly mismatched,
but don't let looks fool you!
Eager to give us all
an encore performance,
we have the Woodpecker!
And his challenger:
Hummingbird!
[GANTA]
I'm sorry...
This is the last thing
I wanted to happen.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
You know the rules, people:
Survival!
Time is no object.
The last combatant
standing wins!
Screw this...! Just... I...
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] Ready...!
Fight like you mean it!
[GANTA] I'm not going to
hurt you, okay? Promise!
But, I want you... to see...
Whip wing!
My Branch of Sin!
You're all the same!
All of you...!
You talk like men but
squeal like virgins!
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] Ho-ho! With
the crack of her fearsome whip,
first blood goes
to Hummingbird!
Not like bumping uglies
with your pal Senji, is it?
Oh... When I'm done
with you, boy,
you're gonna have
nightmares for a month!
That was... just a trick?!
[MINATSUKI LAUGHS]
Please keep making that face!
Oh, god... Oh, my god...
If you new how wet it
was making me right now, ah...!
You'd wish we had escaped.
Everything... everything
you said was crap!
[MINATSUKI]
Well a-derpy der! You dumbass!
Aw... Poor widdle
piggie wiggie...
Why don't you just jack off
in a bottle of formaldehyde
and call it our first born?!
You bitch!
Back down!
[YOH] Ganta!
The hell...?!
That's my sister!
What the...?!
[MINATSUKI] Yo-yo!
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Well, well, well.
We're used to blood
relations in this ring,
just not in this sense...
[GANTA]
I didn't know...
I couldn't have...
Dammit, Minatsuki...
God damn it...
So you're one of
these Deadmen, too?
But why, Yo-yo...?
Why are you...?
[YOH]
Why do you think?!
You're my little sister!
I got myself thrown in
here so I could buy off
the rest of your sentence!
Let go of me...! No!
[G-BLOCK GUARD 6C]
He's being removed, sir.
Hold on...
The audience is liking this.
Little bit of family drama makes
the violence less gratuitous.
[G-BLOCK GUARD 6C] Right.
The key to securing funds
is to make contributors
feel a bit human
once in a while.
I don't believe you.
You got yourself thrown
into this hellhole just...
...just to try
to buy my way out?
Oh...! You're my hero!
The best big brother
a widdle girl like me
could ever hope for!
[GANTA] Would somebody
tell me what's going on?
Because the vibe in here...
[MINATSUKI]
Do you know him?
[YOH] We're in
the same cell...
Though I gotta say I
didn't peg him for someone
who'd raise his
hand to a woman.
What...?! No way!
She basically
tricked me into this--
[GANTA YELLS]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] Whoa!
Woodpecker doesn't look
so nimble, does he folks?
Oh... I'm sorry;
I didn't mean to do that!
Are you okay?
Hey... Take the
temperature of the room...
You might just learn
a thing or two... Dick.
I deserve as much
of the blame as Ganta.
I knew he was my
next opponent...
...and I... I let
myself trust him!
[MINATSUKI CRIES]
What the hell?!
I'm the one
who trusted you!
You're so... dead!
[MINATSUKI THINKING]
That's right, Yo-yo.
Be stupid...
Two blockheaded
little piggie pies...
One of whom is about to
get split down the middle!
[YOH] So... is this
what you did to dad?
Huh...?!
[YOH] Walkin' in on you
like that drove me so far
out of my head...
I lost it.
I blacked out.
All these years I thought
I'd killed the bastard.
Either way the son of
a bitch deserved to die.
You don't think
I did it, do you?
You don't have
to lie anymore.
I finally understand
what you're capable of.
I've seen people with the same
kind of power you have,
little sister...
...so I know
what's out there.
I... know why you
do what you do.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm a freak.
I couldn't care less
about your "powers."
I care about my sister...
It's my job to protect you...
...and that's what
I'm gonna do.
[MINATSUKI]
You dumb fuck...
What are you my goddamn pimp?
You gonna lift your leg
and piss on me next,
or should I just smear your name
in shit across my forehead?!
[MINATSUKI SCREAMS]
This is bullshit!
I... Ugh...!
I can't take it anymore!
If I don't drop
one of you soon,
I won't be able to get off!
You don't get it... do you?
You've probably never
even pleasured a girl.
Minatsuki...
Shut your face!
If you can't get a girl off,
then what the hell
use are you to me?!
[GANTA] Yoh!
[YOH YELLS]
[MINATSUKI LAUGHS]
Forgot to tell
you big brother.
Your sister's a vicious,
murdering little hole! Sorry!
What's it matter?
Everyone's a fucking liar!
If I rip you to shreds,
it's just to keep you
from following my example!
I'll weave a web
of bullshit to rival
every last mother-fucking
one of you assholes!
So next time you wanna
act big, give it a ponder...
Remember that everyone lies!
[YOH GRUNTS]
Or better yet, think of that
floozy cunt you're just like...
God, I hate you!
[GANTA]
Knock it off!
Huh...?
[GANTA] For crying out
loud, that's your brother!
[MINATSUKI] Aaaah...
That's what's up...
You assume this little
piece of shit is your pal...
Well allow me to set you
straight on that, honey.
He doesn't care
if you live or die.
Has he ever bumped
into you on "accident"?
Then afterwards you realized
that something
important was missing?
[GANTA] Yeah...
So what if I did?
[MINATSUKI] Huh...?
[GANTA]
He took 'em for you...
He's been busting his ass
to get you out of this place,
you stupid bitch!
He believed in
your innocence!
Please... Don't...
[GANTA] You really think I
care if he used me to save you?
Oh, You're one of those bleeding
heart queers, aren't you?
"Life is so beautiful,
Minatsuki!
You'd see that if you
just gave it fair shot
every once in a while!"
And when things get ugly,
you're the first person
to turn tail and run...
You think I don't see through
your bullshit, you asshole?!
[GANTA]
Oh, my bullshit...?!
What about yours?!
I'd rather be a liar
than a dumb fuck
who follows his cock
straight into the lion's den!
[GANTA YELLS]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
This is as one-sided a match
as I've ever seen, folks!
Could it be that Woodpecker
has been checkmated?
Ugh...! She's using
Yoh to shield my only in.
I can't do a goddamn thing...
But I still gotta try...
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Hold the phone a minute.
Looks like the boy's got some
retaliation in him yet...
Don't tell me you're
gonna shoot through
your new best friend?
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
A solid miss!
[MINATSUKI LAUGHS]
Is bad aim a strategy?
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Hummingbird is not impressed.
Crap... The hell didn't I eat
something when I had the chance?
You're gonna look
like a train wreck
when I'm done with you!
Just like my filthy,
cock-gnawing whore of a mom!
Listen to you...
Damn it...
That's our mother
you're talking about...
She loved you.
[MINATSUKI] Ugh...
Oh, I'm sorry...
I shouldn't have
used the word "mom."
The cunt actually saved
the fucking primroses...
You believe that shit?!
[MINATSUKI
LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
I... I didn't know...
[MINATSUKI]
Shut your idiot face!
Don't negotiate with the
person who's killing you!
And don't fire at--Ahh!
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Direct hit!
Hummingbird staggers!
And the foolhardy
brother-slash-human shield
is free from her grip!
[MINATSUKI
GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
But she's not done yet!
Something the
Woodpecker looks like
he's just about ready
to learn the hard way...
You are the worst
Deadman I've ever seen.
Branch of Sin
is wasted on you.
[GANTA]
It's wasted on you.
Huh?!
[GANTA] So what if your
mom was a walk-out...?
You gonna spend your whole
damn life twisted about it?
That the best thing you can
think of doing with this power?
[MINATSUKI] Don't you dare talk
down to me! You don't know!
Yeah, well maybe I don't...
Maybe I can't.
But just tell
me one thing...
Why would
you imitate her?
What good's it done?!
[MINATSUKI THINKING]
Seriously?
No way he beat me
with a freaking head-butt!
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
She's down...!
Hummingbird is down!
Woodpecker felled the feisty
little femme fatale with,
of all things,
a butt to the head!
A totally unprecedented
finishing move
for Carnival Corpse!
All of you can
friggin' eat me!
Yeah... That's right,
I said it. Eat me!
I won fair and square,
you four-eyed bastard...
So wrap it the hell up!
Whoa... Did I just
do that...? Damn.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Well, folks; lame as it may be,
since Hummingbird is down,
technically the victory
goes to Woodpecker.
[DIRECTOR LAUGHS]
[DIRECTOR]
What an intriguing child...
Must be the Igarashi blood...
Shiro, my angel, are you
awake by any chance?
Won't you answer
a decrepit old man's need
before another kind
of angel takes him?
The lullaby has ended, my dear.
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA] "Aceman;" a high
tech, pop culture phenomenon
sluiced from the
bowels of T.V. wasteland.
Chances are, as a kid, you
sent off for the decoder ring.
But there's at least
one obscure fact about
everyone's favorite vigilante
even hardcore fans don't know...