[TAMAKI] I think that's
enough viewings for one day.
That's Carnival Corpse
in a nutshell, my boy...
Cast points and
candy if you win...
And if you don't...
much unpleasantry.
You'll be fighting Crow,
again, it seems.
But officially.
You know, the muscley chap.
I hear he even has
biceps on his cock.
But don't let fear
get the better of you.
In a battle royale
between two Deadmen,
mere brute strength isn't
going to carry the day.
[GANTA THINKING] There's no
way I can beat that guy...
[TAMAKI] And... even
if Crow does smear you
into the floorboards...
We'll save whatever we can...
You see...?
We're quite thrifty.
The Director is not
currently receiving visitors.
If you would, please try
again at a more opportune time.
There's something that
I have to ask him...
I'll be quick about it.
[TWINS] That would be
most ill-considered.
[DIRECTOR HUMS]
♪ opening song ♪
[YOH]
Goddamn it!
That rotten bastard...!
If you had any idea
how many cast points
were on those fucking cards!
[SHIRO] Hey!
We have to go back
and save Ganta!
Hey, I'd love to
help him, but--
When they kicked us out, they
locked that door behind us...
And I'm pretty sure
the guards sealed off
that maintenance shaft again.
I don't know if
it's gonna happen.
[SHIRO WHINES]
Man, you're really worried
about the guy, huh?
That's sweet...
But I don't think you
need to stress about it.
With that power of his,
won't he be all right no
matter what he's up against?
[SHIRO WHINES]
He's always been bad
at defending himself!
Yeah, but...
Wait "always"?
Yeah, 'cause...
Ganta isn't very strong.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen!
It's time for another
splatter-filled episode of...
...Carnival Corpse!
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] If you wanna
watch Deadmen duke it out,
we're the only game in town!
The rules are simple!
The fight's over when someone's
incapacitated or dead...!
And now... Meet your Deadmen!
An old hand at
hemoglobin homicide, Crow!
And our plucky young
newcomer, Woodpecker!
[BEAR] Fight card's kinda
lopsided, don't you think?
[SNAKE]
I know, right?
Tossing a rookie in
with Crow? Why bother?
[DIRECTOR] Perhaps... the
boy will surprise us...
[GANTA GASPS]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
Don't puss out...
Woodpecker...
I don't like slicing
myself for nothing!
'Cause as soon that
buzzer goes off...
I'm gonna fuck you up, man...
Little kid or not.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] Ready?
Deadmen... Bleed!
Huh...? Suit yourself...
Just run away
like a little bitch.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] He's making
a dash for it, folks!
We should have
named him Chicken!
[GANTA]
Come on, blood... I need you!
Climbing trees ain't gonna
save you from shit.
Hurry up!
C'mon, it's go-time!
There we go!
Get him!
Dead center!
[GANTA] Shit...!
[SENJI LAUGHS]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] Crow's not
even breaking a sweat!
If that's all Woodpecker's
got, this'll be quick!
[GANTA]
Dammit... Gimmie more...
Yeah, nice and big...
Let's see what
you do with... this!
That one didn't
suck... much.
Huh?!
[BUNNY LAUGHS]
[BUNNY] I think the rookie's
in for an unpleasant surprise!
[SNAKE] Looks to me
like the kid doesn't have
a very firm grip on his branch.
Man, I'm... freezing...
Guess that's about right
for a kid your size...
You been attacking me
with those projectiles...
Figured you'd be
safer far away. Heh.
I mean, it only makes sense.
But still, ya been shooting
your blood at me...
You kinda need to
hang on to that shit
to stay alive, remember?
[GANTA GASPS]
You keep slinging your blood
around like it's infinite...
...and it's gonna
be lights-out.
[GANTA]
I... I can't... s-see...!
[BUNNY] Ha, ha! Is he gonna
start drunk-boxing? Spare me.
[BEAR] And Crow
hasn't even hit him yet.
Y'know, if Crow's
going to win anyway,
I at least want my wife
to get to see him in action!
[TAKASHIMA]
An adult male can handle losing
about two liters of blood.
But a boy his size
will fall into shock
if he loses more than
a liter and a half.
Ah... What happens then?
[TAKASHIMA]
Nothing. He dies.
[TAMAKI LAUGHS]
[GANTA] I can't...
I can't... pass out...
[SENJI] You can tell
yourself whatever you want.
But you've hit your limit
and you damn well know it.
[RUMBLING]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] And down comes
Woodpecker, cradle and all!
No way...
How is he doing that?!
I'm gonna end your
short, pathetic life, kiddo.
How does he have...
that much blood?
This is the part
where I take you out!
[GANTA YELLS]
Stop the presses!
Woodpecker is in peril!
[BUZZING]
[TAKASHIMA]
Good news, Tamaki.
The lab just got back
to me about that... thing.
How vague of you.
[TAKASHIMA] The object
inside 5580's chest.
Do tell.
Turns out...
...its composition
matches exactly that
of the crystals from
the epicenter...
We figured as much...
but now we know for sure.
[TAMAKI] Uh-huh.
I'm afraid that's all we
can tell at the present.
But if that isn't enough...
I'll need to get more hands-on.
I bet.
Well... he is on death-row,
just like the rest of them.
When he loses, fillet him
to your heart's content.
Flimsy toys...
How they vex me.
[GANTA BREATHES HEAVILY]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER]
Put the kids to bed!
The fat lady's about to sing!
Come on...
...or was the hit that
cracked my sternum yesterday
just a one-off?!
[SENJI]
Wake the fuck up.
Carnival Corpse...
...ain't something
you're gonna win
by acting like a
scared little pussy.
[GANTA THINKING]
It hurts... I'm scared...
I... I'm just... done.
How'd it... even come to this?
[KID GANTA]
It hurts... It really hurts!
[KID SHIRO] Ganta... How come
you're being such a wimp?
[GANTA THINKING] Shiro...?
[KID SHIRO]
You're so weak. It's no fun.
[GANTA'S MOM]
Try to be patient with him.
You're a lot stronger
than the other children.
[SHIRO]
Whenever something bad happens,
he starts crying right away.
Maybe so... but you
should really try
to cut the guy
a little more slack.
The overwhelming majority
of us can't drop-kick robots.
[BIRD ANNOUNCER] This fight
has panned out pretty much
exactly how the
odds-makers figured.
Apologies, folks.
[KID GANTA GRUNTS]
[SHIRO] Oh...!
I just remembered...
Know what makes
Ganta so amazing?
[KID GANTA GRUNTS]
He always gets up again!
Look at you! Heh...
[GANTA]
I can't... die yet...
I need to find...
the Red Man...
...and avenge my friends.
I don't understand...
why my blood does this.
It hurts... And I'm scared...
But I...
I don't want to go down...
Not without a fight!
Do you hear me?!
I'm not lying down!
[SENJI LAUGHS]
That's what I'm talking about!
He's running on sheer willpower!
[GANTA YELLS]
[BIRD ANNOUNCER YELLS]
[SENJI] As if!
[CRASHING SOUND]
Ooh!
Damn, kid!
[GANTA] Stop it...
I have a name!
It's Ganta...!
Ganta Igarashi!
[SENJI] Good job...
Ya hit me dead center...
The kid's... got a pair...
[THUD]
[GANTA BREATHES HEAVILY]
We're finally back
on the map...
[SHIRO] Hey, I wanna
see Ganta again.
C'mon, slowpoke!
[INFORMANT] Just the
man I wanted to see.
Check it out.
I tracked down that information
you've been looking for.
Really?!
[INFORMANT]
That chick you described...
There's a girl in the basement
that looks exactly like her.
[YOH]
The basement...?!
You mean G Block?!
[INFORMANT]
Mmm... So you know.
Most folks, don't
know it exists.
How to get in...?
Please tell me you
know how to get in!
Oh, I can tell you...
But it's gonna cost
you... extra.
[INFORMANT CHUCKLES]
G Block... Back we go.
[SHIRO] ♪ Ga! Ga! Ganta fight!
Knock 'em dead, Ganta! Hey! ♪
♪ Shi! Shi! Shiro is feeling
good, now shake it! ♪
♪ Ga! Ga! Ganta fight!
Knock 'em dead, Ganta! Hey! ♪
♪ Shi! Shi! Shiro is-- ♪
What in the holy hell
are you singing?
That's Ganta's
fight song.
If you keep making noise,
the guards are gonna find us!
Aww... I guess I'll
stop singing, then.
I miss Ganta and I
wanna see him, though.
[YOH] Alright. But we
gotta be quiet like ninjas.
I believe in you, Shiro.
Quietest ninja ever!
[FEMALE ANCHOR 5-A] And now,
here's a rundown on tomorrow's
weather forecast for
the Kanto region.
Tokyo and Kanagawa
will both be sunny
with a chance of clouds
later in the day.
Saitama and Chiba should
remain sunny all day long--
you sun-bathers know
which prefectures to hit up.
Meanwhile, sporadic
showers and gusty winds
throughout Gunma and Tochigi
might put a damper
on your weekend.
Ugh, it's so bad!
But I... gotta eat it to live.
[FEMALE ANCHOR 5-A]
As always, we'll be here with
the latest weather updates to
get you through the weekend.
[SENJI]
Hey... Champ.
Look... I, uh...
Hell of a fight.
Much respect, Ganta.
[GANTA] Yeah!
[FEMALE ANCHOR 5-A] Thanks
for watching news at eight.
I was so afraid
of him... but...
[GAME SHOW MUSIC]
Maybe... me and Senji
are gonna be okay now...
Hey! What's
clucking, everyone?
It's time for the Carnival
Corpse post-game treat!
It's... the "Too Bad
for the Loser Show!"
Huh...?
Wait, that's...
Hi there, Senji.
I hope your luck has
improved since the fight.
Hold up...
What's going on?
[SENJI] Just do it.
[TAKASHIMA]
The right eye.
Huh...?
[GANTA GASPS]
[SENJI YELLS IN AGONY]
[SENJI BREATHES HEAVILY]
[GANTA RETCHES]
[EXPLOSION]
What... the hell?!
[SHIRO YELLS ANGRILY]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
--What's happening up there?!
--[SHIRO] Don't take me away
from Ganta, you meanies!
[GUARD 5-A CHOKES]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
This is control...!
What's going on here?!
SR-4...!
Come in, dammit!
[YOH]
Armed uprising, sir!
We're gonna need back-up ASAP!
If they force their
way into the system...!
You gotta shut down
the electricity
in this cell-block... please!
[CONTROL TOWER
COMMANDER] Understood!
Armored guards are
on their way.
But who's running the show?
How many perps
are we talking here?!
There's only one, sir...
Just a single, solitary
girl with snow-white hair.
[Instrumental "Lullaby"]
Damn it, that little
girl is insane!
I don't like how it got
quiet all of a sudden.
Where the hell is she?
The lullaby... it stopped.
[GUNS COCK]
[GUARD DETAIL LEADER]
Perpetrator confirmed!
Extreme prejudice, gentlemen!
[DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN]
I really owe you one, Shiro!
Thanks a lot for being a decoy
and distracting 'em all for me.
[EXPLOSION]
[THUD]
[GANTA RETCHES]
[GANTA COUGHS]
[THUD]
[GANTA THINKING]
You forgot...
Stupid...
[GANTA THINKING]
It's a madhouse...
...and you're locked inside it.
[YOH GASPS]
[GANTA THINKING]
You can't forget... Not ever...
This is real...
This is your whole world now...
Deadman Wonderland...
That's what they call it...
But really... it's hell.
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA] When the lullaby
ends and the egg laughs...
...the world will
drown in absurdity.
Branch of Sin is
different for everybody...
You can look at the flower
all you want, Woodpecker...
...but mind those thorns.