[MAKINA]
Two-thousand twenty-three...
The savage mass murder of over
two dozen middle school children
in a Nagano classroom has led
to the arrest and conviction
of fourteen year-old
Ganta Igarashi.
Horror stricken and
paralyzed with grief,
the shell-shocked boy
stood helpless as
the wheels of "justice" ground
his claims of innocence to dust.
Now, behind the ironclad walls
of Japan's first and
only publicly-funded,
coliseum-style penal colony,
he struggles to make sense of
the cruel trick played
on him by fate...
All for your personal amusement.
[FIREWORKS]
[MAKINA]
That odd glow...
Is it actually coming from him?
[TAMAKI] The plan to have
a fatal accident befall
Ganta Igarashi has been
summarily abandoned.
Retool your approach
accordingly, please...
We'll see how he
fares on his own.
Something tells me...
we can expect a lot.
[MAKINA THINKING]
Oily son of a bitch.
Three inmates die in your
attempt on his life,
and you're wringing your hands?
Who's this kid anyway...?
Why should I give a damn?
What are you planning to
squeeze out of him, Tamaki?
♪ opening song ♪
[GANTA THINKING] When the
Red Man butchered my friends...
...it's like he hacked
the whole world to pieces
right along with 'em.
All I know now is that I don't
want to die in this hellhole.
'Kay... Now try
to keep still.
[GANTA YELLS]
[GANTA] Son of a...
[TAKASHIMA] You're young,
so that's in our favor...
You'll heal up quickly.
Uh... Thank you
for patchin' me up.
Now... my records show
you're a death row inmate.
Yeah...
I assume you've been
eating your candy.
My what?
The first piece
was in your bag.
You did find it,
didn't you?
Uh...
You should've been given
a "survival kit" upon admission.
A duffle bag.
Oh... I don't know if
it had any candy in it.
[TAKASHIMA]
I'd look again if I were you.
Granted it tastes pretty foul,
but you learn to choke it down.
[YOH] You know...
I bet it fell out...
I did bash into you pretty
solid with that cart.
You again.
[YOH SCREAMS]
Sorry, man...
If you feel like breakin' my
nose, I'll totally understand.
S'fine... I don't have
much of a sweet tooth.
Anyway, I'm more
worried about you.
[YOH] I'll live.
All she did was give
me a flesh wound.
[GANTA] Still, though.
She really unloaded on you.
It's just how things are...
but you do adjust
to it after a while.
You may hate 'em, and they sure
as hell don't make much sense...
following the rules
is how you get by.
Apparently.
[GRATE RATTLES]
Play with me, Ganta!
[GANTA AND YOH YELL]
Vampire!
I'm not a vampire...
I'm Ganta's very bestest buddy!
Oh... I'm sorry...
I've just never seen you before.
[GANTA] Yeah...
I told her the same
thing yesterday.
Know what...?
We should enter
the race as a team!
Huh?
They've got these big
toys spread out all over...
It's so awesome!
Ah...
I'm readin' ya...
I think she
means the dog race.
The what race?
It's one of the
attractions that they run
to dig up tourist scratch.
Folks pay out the ass to see it.
Oh, I get it... I think.
[YOH] The dog race is like
a marathon obstacle course.
The prize is, like...
a hundred thousand cast points.
[GANTA] Holy...
Wait, what...?
The hell's a cast point?
[YOH]
Hold on, seriously...?
You've read the rulebook, right?
[GANTA]
Uh... Not yet, no.
[YOH]
Okay, pay attention...
Cast points are basically
Deadman Wonderland's
form of currency.
You followin' me?
[GANTA] Sure...
Uhh...
[YOH] Trust me, you can't
take 'em for granted.
There are no free
lunches in this joint.
The flip side is that virtually
nothing's contraband
if you have the cast.
Cigarettes.
Booze. You name it...
Rat-hole enough points
away and you can even
buy off increments
of your sentence.
[SHIRO] Huh?
[YOH] Are you kidding?
You must be new here, too.
Oh, I see...
So I've got to earn
some cast points.
It's prob'ly not
too late for you to
enter the race
if you want.
Yeah maybe... But I'm
not much of an athlete.
[GANTA'S STOMACH GROWLS]
You get a red bean
bun for participating.
Then I'll do it!
Yay!
Red bean bun!
Red bean bun...!
[GANTA]
Will you calm down already?
And stop pushing me...
People are gonna think--
Red bean bun!
[MAKINA] What is this?
I'm talking to you...
Five-five-eight-zero.
Uh... Well, I'm...
...on my way to
the dog race.
[MAKINA]
As an entry...? Excellent...
So you've read chapter
eleven in your rulebook.
Uh... Sure... Yeah...
I know the whole thing by heart.
[MAKINA] Good... Understanding
how we run things here
is what keeps wolves
in sheeps' clothing alive.
[PHONE RINGS]
[YOH] Mr. Tamaki?
It's Yoh Takami.
I'm calling to report
on the new guy.
Yes sir... It looks like he's
planning to enter today's race.
[FIREWORKS]
[PARK ANNOUNCER LADY]
Attention park visitors:
Deadman Wonderland's
legendary Dog Race
hits the ground running
in twenty minutes!
You won't want to miss
this action-packed,
thrill-a-minute spectacular,
so wag those tails
to the stadium pronto!
Oh, hi.
Hey there. Do you
mind if I join you?
But... What about
your injury?
[YOH] What about it?
Cast points are cast points.
Yeah... I guess
you're right.
Let's start over...
The name's Yoh Takami...
My friends call me Yoh.
Ah... Yoh it is...
Ganta Igarashi.
It's a pleasure... Igarashi.
Just Ganta... Please,
I'm a death row inmate...
Whatever, man...
I got something for you.
[PRISONERS GASP FEARFULLY]
More balls in this
shithouse than I thought.
They grow outta the walls
for a hundred thousand cast.
[LACKEY 2-C] Ha!
Greedy assholes, all of ya!
Oh no...
We are screwed.
Crap... Okay, say
goodbye to your chance.
[PRISONER 2-C] To your
ass, more like. I'm out!
[PRISONER 2-D]
I'm with him!
[GANTA] I know that guy...
[YOH] Kazumasa Kouzuji...
Have you ever heard
of mixed martial arts?
You'd need a whole week to
melt down all his gold medals.
[GANTA] Whoa... You mean
that's "The Pulverizer?"
Yeah...
He's in here 'cause he got
really mad at an actress.
Some chick he met
on a reality show
who wouldn't exchange
email addresses with him.
Huh...?
Your face screams
newcomer, kid...
You just
off the boat?
[GANTA]
Uh, Yes...
[KOUZUJI]
"Yes, Kouzuji."
Oh... Right...
I recognize--
[GANTA YELLS]
Holy crap!
[LACKEYS LAUGH]
You shitheads forget
how to show respect?!
Clear a path when you see
me walkin' into a room!
And wipe those stupid
looks off your faces!
I just gave you gold...
You should be laughing...
That was some funny shit!
Huh...?
Let's try this again.
[YOH SCREAMS]
Yoh...
Pay attention,
you jackholes...
Bow out of this race
and you'll answer to me.
They'll cancel the damn
thing if more of you bail...
And I want those cast points!
You idiots understand?!
And don't think about
winning 'em for yourselves...
Take your treat and
scuttle back to your cell.
[LACKEY 2-C] The rule
is stay out of his way!
[LACKEY 2-B]
If you get it... stand aside!
[LACKEY 2-A]
Move it, princess!
[PRISONER 2-C YELLS]
[PRISONER 2-D YELLS]
[LACKEY 2-B LAUGHS]
[BLOWS LAND]
These guys are animals.
[KOUZUJI]
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
[GANTA GASPS]
[GANTA YELLS FEARFULLY]
Coulda sworn I heard
you make a comment.
Huh...? No, I... No!
Did you say we were animals?
Y'mean the
party kind, right?
Is that what you meant?
Aw, c'mon, show me the face
of someone who enjoys a party.
[GANTA THINKING] I don't want
to die... Not like this.
Show me you know how
to have a good time.
[GANTA THINKING] If I want to
stay alive in this place...
...I'm gonna have
to fall in line.
[GANTA LAUGHS]
[GANTA THINKING]
Way to go... Coward.
[KOUZUJI]
Not half bad, kid.
[GANTA GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[LACKEYS LAUGH]
[SHIRO]
Look at what I got!
We should totally chow
down before the race...
What are you doing?
[KOUZUJI] Huh...?!
Do you have a tummy ache?
[LACKEY 2-B]
You little bitch!
[SHIRO] Huh?
Those big eyes...
Just like the stupid
cunt who put me in here!
[UNSHEATHING SOUND]
Ah... Chief
Warden Makina...
Was that over the top?
[MAKINA]
We've been over this...
How long you gonna keep it up?
Till I get a piece
of that fine ass.
[MAKINA]
Is that a fact?
Then you should
make a move...
When you're
ready to die.
[GUARD 2-A] Time is up!
All of you into the arena
with your number tag!
[KOUZUJI] Someday, I'm
gonna fuck you in half.
I got us a cookie.
[CHEWING]
[SHIRO GIGGLES]
"Unless they wish to
succumb to poisoning,
death row inmates must ingest
candy every three days...
This temporarily counteracts
the stream of poison
being pumped into their necks."
Man, that's pretty messed up.
[SHIRO] You don't even
want a little bite?
I'm gonna eat the whole
thing if you don't.
[GANTA] "Cost per unit is
one-hundred-thousand cast."
Eat candy every three days...
Or essentially I guess...
...my sentence is
pretty much served.
It looks like I've
got a race to win.
[TAMAKI]
My source's intel was spot on.
Looks like the
boy's raring to go.
[SUPERVISOR] Is there some way
I can be of service to you?
[TAMAKI] Yeah...
Let's ratchet up the stakes
to maximum kill for today...
We'll need a corpse
disposal team...
Oh... Be sure to tell all
the human rights vermin
it's strictly theatre.
[SUPERVISOR] But there will be
children in the audience today!
[TAMAKI] All the more reason to
work the "performance" angle,
wouldn't you say?
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Welcome to one
of the most
hackle-raising events
Deadman Wonderland has
to offer: The Dog Race!
With a whopping one hundred
thousand cast grand prize,
the stakes are high
and the tension electric!
[GUNSHOT]
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
And they're off!
[GANTA THINKING]
Think about the cast points.
Think about the antidote.
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Trampling fiercely toward the
first obstacle, our contestants
are about to find out
who can keep their heads...
...in The Slicer!
[GANTA]
Huh? What is this?
[SPLAT]
[PRISONER 2-F SCREAMS]
[GANTA THINKING]
Holy shit...
[SPECTATORS CHEER]
[PRISONERS YELL WORRIEDLY]
[GUNSHOTS]
[SPECTATORS CHEER]
Dude, their
effects rock!
Told you it'd be cool.
[SPECTATOR LADY 2-A]
Ugh. This is making me sick.
[SPECTATOR 2-C]
Aw, it's part of the show.
...'sides, how stupid you gotta
be to think this cheese is real?
Hell, even if it was...
...they're friggin' criminals.
[GANTA THINKING] What the hell
is wrong with these people?
Are they getting
off watching us die?
[GAME EMCEE MAN] And now the
Bone-crushing Bungie Bungle...
...where a hasty
choice in ropes...
[LOUD THUD]
...leads ya all the way down!
[GANTA THINKING]
No... No...
I can't handle this.
[GANTA YELLS]
Hold on...!
Wait!
[SHIRO]
C'mon... Deep breath.
[GANTA] You've got
to be kidding me!
[CLASPING SOUND]
[GANTA SCREAMS]
Holy shiiiiiiiit!
[SHIRO] Ta-da!
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
You've seen 'em slide,
you've seen 'em swing,
now you'll see 'em
"suffer the slings and arrows
of outrageous fortune"
in Archer's Alley!
[PRISONERS YELL WORRIEDLY]
[PRISONER 2-J SCREAMS]
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Looks like somebody's strayed
from the straight and narrow!
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[GANTA THINKING]
Oh man, that smell.
[GANTA YELLS]
[SHIRO] Helloooo! Ha!
[GANTA SCREAMS]
You gotta move
around more, friend!
[GANTA] Cut it out, Shiro!
You're gonna make me fall!
[KOUZUJI] Heh.
What the...?
Hey! The hell
you doing?!
Sorry, fellas...
but this game
is worth a lot more
than cast points.
[LACKEYS YELL IN PAIN]
[LACKEY 2-B]
You rat bastard!
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[SHIRO LAUGHS]
[PRISONER 2-M] Ahh!
[PRISONERS GROAN IN AGONY]
[GANTA]
I think I'm done.
[SHIRO] But we're so close
to getting red bean buns!
I didn't even do anything...
...and they still send
me to a place like this.
I try to follow the rules,
but it doesn't do any good.
No matter what I do,
I get screwed.
The rules...?
Hey... Sometimes I have
a rule of just one snack a day.
But when
I feel like it...
I say to heck with it and
eat as many as I want to.
I don't have that luxury.
That's just... That's just
the way things are here.
Unless I'm willing
to throw in the towel,
I have to be on my toes...
...to try to guess
what's coming next.
Even when that's impossible.
That really doesn't
sound like fun...
Oh...! I think
I understand now.
That's like your
personal rule.
[GANTA YELLS]
[SHIRO LAUGHS]
[GANTA BREATHES HEAVILY]
So fun...!
We're number one!
Now we're gonna eat...
a Red bean bun!
Red bean bun!
Look at 'em...
Man... I can't believe
this was somebody's idea
of a field trip for us.
Huh...?
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Now, the battle royale
you've all been waiting for!
Whoever's left standing with
the Deadman Ball in his hands
walks away with
one-hundred thousand cast!
[SHIRO]
This'll be so much fun!
[GANTA]
Wait... Left standing...?
Crap, does that mean
what I think it does?!
[GAME EMCEE MAN] Begin!
[GANTA SCREAMS]
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
That's right: the game ends
when the final tile drops
and the contestant lucky
enough to have the ball
and not be impaled
is the winner!
[SPECTATORS CHEER]
[GANTA YELLS]
[KOUZUJI YELLS]
[SHIRO] Huh...?
Gotta hand it
to you, pipsqueak;
you've got bigger reserves of
badass than I was counting on.
But I get
your persistence.
That face...
Hell, how could anyone miss it
'less they'd been
living under a rock...?
Not everyday ya get to rub
shoulders with a celebrity.
[SHIRO] Ganta! I'm wide open!
[KOUZUJI] Will you
fucking fall already?!
Look, kid...
You're on death row,
why are you fightin'
so hard to survive?
[GANTA]
'Cause... I'm innocent.
[KOUZUJI] Shit, I know a
killer when I see one, psycho!
Ask me, you shouldn't even
be allowed to compete...
[SHIRO] Give it!
[KOUZUJI] Tell you what, why
don't I cut you a little deal?
Be a good sport and die now,
and I won't feed you
your own pancreas later on.
[GANTA]
I'm only going to say this once.
[KOUZUJI] Huh...?
[KOUZUJI YELLS]
I am not a
freaking murderer!
You think I'm scared of some
loudmouth dickwad like you...
...after the
shit I've seen?!
So if you're going to kill me...
Stop wasting my
damn time and do it!
'Cause while I'm breathing...
This place and its rules
can suck my dick!
[SHIRO] Good one!
You are one dead
little piece of shit!
Ahh...!
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Contestant forty-six has
botched her surefooted sashay
and is going downtown!
[KOUZUJI]
Aww... crap.
Ah!
[KOUZUJI YELLS]
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Stalwart number ninety-three
has taken the plunge!
[GANTA] Shiro!
[SHIRO LAUGHS]
[GANTA THINKING] Wait, you...
You were protecting me?
No!
Ganta...! Catch!
[GANTA THINKING] Oh god...
[GAME EMCEE MAN]
Things are really lookin'
good for number seven!
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[DEFLATING HISS]
Ganta, what's wrong?
The ball...
Who cares about that?
We still get to eat, right?
Yeah... We do!
[GANTA THINKING] No one
wins the dog race today...
Which is fine by me.
This game sucks anyway.
So I don't get the
antidote, or candy,
or whatever it's called.
I don't care anymore.
Even if tomorrow
is my third day.
Let my sentence
be carried out.
[SHIRO LAUGHS]
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA]
Avenging the friends you've seen
fall to a bloodthirsty madman
buys you a one-way ticket to
the heart of Deadman Wonderland;
a heart beating to the
rhythm of strange magic
and even stranger people...