Heads up, Ganta!
[OHARA]
Karako!
What are you doing?!
Don't stand around!
Get out of here!
No, you--Wait!
We can take the
sonofabitch down!
[AKIYAMA]
There isn't time! Forget it!
[GANTA]
We can't leave her!
Karako!
It's all you... Ganta.
[BELL CHIMES]
♪ opening song ♪
[MATAYOSHI]
Karako Koshio, huh...?
The "Game Fowl" herself...
[KOUMOTO] Who makes a nutcase
their damn second-in-command?
Seriously, did Nagi lose
his marbles or something?
[ENDOU] I'd keep it
down if I were you...
If there's a cockfight,
she's gonna win.
[OHARA]
She can totally hear you!
[BELL CHIMES]
[NAGI]
What a beautiful sound.
It's a cheap little
bell--dime a dozen.
And yet it
lends me assurance.
However grim
the circumstances...
if the chiming of that little
bell can reach my ears...
then I'll know that quite
a woman has my back.
[NAGI] It warms me
like the light of day,
even in the darkness
of this basement.
Who ever said I was
joining up, smooth-talker?
No one... but you came
here for a reason.
[NAGI] I first noticed it
dangling around your neck
while bracing across
from you on the mat.
And when I heard
it jingle, I knew...
There's quite a bit
more to this gal
than her chops
as a warrior.
Call it a hunch.
Which is why I want you
to be our number two.
All because of a
cheap little bell, huh?
That's right.
[KARAKO LAUGHS]
God, what a fool...
Did they all get across?
[NECRO MACRO WHIRS]
Asshole.
[KARAKO THINKING]
What did I want outta life?
I wanted you.
[STEAM HISSES]
[NECRO MACRO WHIRS]
[KARAKO]
Tough titty, huh?
As it turns out I'm a stone-cold
bitch on offense and defense.
[KARAKO THINKING]
Know what, Nagi?!
Even if what we're
fighting for is bunk...
nothing but a
stupid pipe-dream...!
Goddamn it! I'm all in.
I might get to make
it outside again...
but if I die right here...
So fucking be it.
[CRASHING SOUND]
Karako's okay back there...
She is, right?
She's tough... Ain't no
point worrying about her.
[GANTA]
Yeah, but...
I mean, we just
left her behind...
Look, Ganta...
Karako knew what was at stake.
Right.
The Undertakers are
probably on their way...
I sure don't wanna be
here when they show up.
They may not
be clued in yet...
If they were, this whole
block would be on lockdown.
Besides,
Wakabayashi and Miyako
are ready to lead them
on a wild goose chase.
[HARUMI] This is the
elevator we need to take...
It's our one-way ticket
outta Deadman Wonderland.
Sounds pretty
straightforward...
But Nagi and Rokuro
have to send it down
from the control
room, don't they?
That's right kid.
If those doors
open, then we know
those two were able to
get the job done up there.
[NAGI AND ROKURO
BREATHE HEAVILY]
How you holding up,
Rokuro...? You good?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Then let's get that
service elevator activated...
If all is going
well down there,
they should be waiting
for it even as we speak.
[SQUEAKING]
Little girl...
What on earth are
you doing in here?
It's a pleasure
to meet you...
My name is Hibana.
Listen to you...
That is a very polite greeting
from someone so young...
How old are you, dear?
I'm actually in the
second-grade, mister...
And I just
finished my homework...
So it's time to do my
chores like a young lady.
The plot thickens,
it seems...
I daresay you're
lost... Rokuro...
Send down the
elevator, would you?
I'm sure the
others are there.
[ROKURO] Hmm...
Listen--you aren't
safe here...
I think you ought
to come with us.
[ROKURO LAUGHS]
Rokuro... What are
you waiting for?!
Sorry, fearless leader,
but there's been a
slight change of plans.
What are
you talking about?
[CRACKING]
Shoulda checked my work when
you had me crunch the numbers.
[HIBANA]
Down you go...!
I'm the commander of the
3rd Undertaker Battalion...
I'm here because you...
have been a very naughty boy.
Do what you must.
Yet another thing
I'll regret having to do.
My apologies, little one.
My branch of sin!
[CRASHING SOUND]
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Now all your sins
will be burned down
to ash in the 21st
dimension of Isgorchia...
So then you won't have
the naughty blood anymore...
And nobody'll
call you the Owl...
because you won't have
special powers after we're done.
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[NAGI THINKING]
Blood negation...
Ganta warned us of this...
[NAGI]
You bastard.
You manipulated the
footage... didn't you?
[HIBANA]
Surprise, mister!
Wanna know a secret?
There's a thing in my
sword called Worm Eater.
It oxidizes the
virus in your blood.
You can attack me with
your branch of sin,
but it's just
gonna disintegrate.
All us Undertakers
have it in our weapons.
That's pretty
nifty, isn't it?!
Thanks for explaining.
[HIBANA LAUGHS]
Well, a lady is
honest with her foe.
[ROKURO LAUGHS]
You're at a disadvantage...
Wouldn't you agree?
The Undertakers all have
their brains bad-touched...
That's where they
wrench out their mercy
and empathy and
all that shit...
So how 'bout we make
this easy on everyone?
[NAGI THINKING]
Failure is not an option.
Their dreams...
And mine... Too much
hangs in the balance!
Someone didn't listen!
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[OOTAKE]
What's keeping 'em?
It hasn't moved
an inch yet.
Oh Nagi...
and Rokuro...
...please be okay.
[GANTA THINKING]
Now what...?
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[HIBANA]
Shame on you, mister...!
Running around,
getting blood on everything!
But it's nothing that a little
tough love can't fix right up!
[NAGI THINKING]
You little imp...!
You need a lot
more punishing huh...
But Genkaku told me that
killing you would
be a big no-no...
[ROKURO] You keep thumpin'
the shit outta him...
he's gonna die whether
you want him to or not.
[ROKURO LAUGHS]
[HIBANA]
No going easy on him!
Listen, you!
You're getting punished
until I hear a proper apology!
Heh! She don't beat
around the bush, does she?
You're might wanna
say you're sorry
before she
breaks your neck.
I realize that you're
not my daughter...
But I'm not about
to just overlook...
such ill-mannered
behavior from one so young.
How about... I give
you the Lingering Death!
Uh-oh...
She's about to get creative.
Don't know what that is...?
You shoulda hit
the books a little harder!
Fine I'll tell you.
The Lingering Death is a method
of execution that China used
until late into
the Ching Dynasty...
They'd cut a person apart,
but they'd be super
careful about it...
First, they'd slice the
flesh off the person's chest...
And then, off of the
arms... and the stomach...
an' thighs...
even the bottom...
I wonder how many cuts
I can give you?
If I'm really careful, I betcha
I can cut you 3,000 times!
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
If you're worried about
bleeding out, mister...
...don't be!
Cause you're gonna get
scared in a minute or two...
and scared people don't
bleed nearly as much!
[ROKURO YAWNS]
I'm telling ya,
the dude's gonna die.
He'll be okay!
Without pain,
how can we ever become
the upstanding citizens
we're supposed to be?!
That's what Mama thought,
and I think I
turned out pretty well!
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
You'll mature into a perfect
gentleman before you know it...
Prob'ly even before I
even lop off your face!
That was you, wasn't it...
a couple of years ago...
The one who cut her whole
kindergarten class
into ribbons...
Well as a lady... it is my
duty to punish the wicked.
"Lady"... you said...?
A lady would never
butcher children.
What you are, under the
very best of circumstances...
is a mewling little
hellion of a girl.
I feel pity for you...
A tattered scrap of
humanity--that's all you are.
Mama's special
little punching-bag.
[HIBANA]
I am not... a little brat!
Hibana is... a lady!
[CRASHING SOUNDS]
[HIBANA GRUNTS]
[NAGI GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[HIBANA'S MOTHER] Wretched girl!
You've wet the bed, again!
As punishment, we must return
the piss to
the 17th dimension--
to the seat of the hizamoro,
from whence it came!
[HIBANA]
Yes, Mama... I'm sorry.
[HIBANA'S MOTHER]
Wretched girl!
How dare you vomit up
perfectly good mushrooms?!
As punishment, we have to seal
the three holes within
Battenoro's orbit at once!
[HIBANA]
Yes, Mama... I'm sorry.
[HIBANA GRUNTS]
I did punish them
properly, didn't I?
My mama taught me...!
She taught me so well,
I taught her right back!
I don't pee the bed anymore!
I love mushrooms--I love 'em!
[NAGI GRUNTS]
I'm a lady, just like Mama!
[NAGI SCREAMS]
You call that
punishment, do you?
Don't make me laugh.
I won't be felled by
a couple of scratches...
What kind of a weakling
do you take me for?!
[HIBANA YELLS]
Stop it or I'm
gonna cut off that one!
Sure you
wanna do that?
Huh...?
[NAGI] Should've
put your toys away...
[HIBANA YELLS WORRIEDLY]
I apologize for what
I'm about to do to you.
You little bitch.
Here we go.
They pulled it off!
Heh! Good job!
[KOSUGI]
Let's get a move on, guys!
Rokuro and Nagi
sure delivered!
You hang onto
that data chip...
Nice and tight.
[GANTA] I will!
[OOTAKE] I wonder how I'm
gonna get by on the outside...
Come an' work at my factory.
Hell, maybe I should
tag along too...
Finally get to
scope out this wife
you're always
going on about.
Don't blame me
if ya fall in love!
[YAMAZAKI LAUGHS]
Yeah, but what if she
falls in love with Ueshima?
[ENDOU LAUGHS]
If my wife is steppin' out...
it's gonna be with
a hotter guy than him!
[GROUP LAUGHS]
[GENKAKU]
Hey assholes, laugh it up!
Think it's time
I played you off.
[GUNSHOTS]
[YELLING]
Hmm...?
What the fuck, fellas?
Where's the albino?
[KOSUGI]
Damn Undertaker!
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
Duuude... Uber-monk.
[ENDOU YELLS]
The branch of sin...
It didn't--
[OHARA] Harumi!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[GANTA YELLS]
[GUNSHOT]
[AKIYAMA GROANS]
[ROKURO] I'm impressed,
not gonna lie...
The odds of you actually
defeating that kid
and sending the elevator
down to the others
were something
like fifty to one.
Am I to assume...
you sicced the Undertakers
on the others as well?
[ROKURO]
Dude, you have to ask?
Whatever you do...
I know the others
will manage to smuggle
that data-chip
out of this place.
[ROKURO] They've got a
one-fifth of one percent chance.
More than enough...
when dreams are on the line...
Even if the odds
were infinitely worse...
That's a bet I would take.
[ROKURO LAUGHS]
You must've hit your
head when you fell down...
'Cause I've been busting
my ass to make sure
that never fucking happens,
you sorry sack o' shit!
Tamaki knew what you
were up to all along.
You played right into his hands.
Just so you know,
my calculations are legit.
I mean, there were
a lot of easier ways
to take Scar Chain out...
but the boss insisted
on a spectacle...
Man... Undertakers are killing
your friends even as we speak.
[NAGI SHUDDERS]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
What was that for?
You protect this data-chip
with your life, Ganta!
Just get it to
the outside world!
[KOSUGI GASPS]
[KOSUGI YELLS]
Show them... the truth...
You are Scar Chain... now...
Ganta!
Does freedom look
like that to you, Ganta?
Something harsh?
[GANTA THINKING]
They gave their lives...
everything they had...
for the sake of the truth!
Even if it kills me...
the world is gonna know!
[NAGI GRUNTS]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[NAGI] If any...
anyone... can hear me...
Please, just... listen...
I wanna sleep but
it's too noisy...
An' I'm so hungry...
Hey, Ganta?
Huh?... Hey, who're you?
[OOTAKE SCREAMS]
[GANTA GASPS]
[GENKAKU LAUGHS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GANTA YELLS]
You might want to
think of a back-up plan
if you're waitin'
for Aceman.
Speaking of everyone's
favorite superhero,
didja know the series was
supposed to end differently?
[GANTA YELLS]
The villains all put
their heads together,
and decide to kill
everyone but Aceman...
They proceed to stack those
bastards up like cordwood.
Shut up...
I think they should have
aired it as-is, don't you?
Why sugar-coat it?
Leave me alone!
Our lives are nothing
more than suffering.
Why hammer it into the
kiddies' heads one at a time
when you can teach
'em all at once?!
[GENKAKU LAUGHS]
Sorry, Genkaku...
But it's time to go.
Catch ya later, kid.
You'll get your private show.
I got a song
that'll knock you dead.
What the
hell was that?!
C'mon, you guys--
this is our chance!
Ganta, it's time to go!
[GANTA] Okay!
[STEAM HISSES]
Shiro, what were
you doing in there?!
I told you to wait!
What's going on?
Why do you look scared?
Listen, Ganta...!
You gotta give me the
data chip right now!
Hold on, what're you...?
[GANTA] Wait, how do
you know about the--?!
Hey...! Gimmie that!
Shiro!
[SHIRO GRUNTS]
[EXPLOSION]
[GROUP GASPS]
Ganta... I'm so
glad you're okay!
♪ closing song ♪
[MAKINA]
Insanity feeds on itself...
gives birth to itself anew...
It doesn't matter how much
the weak piss and moan,
they still end up
as cannon fodder...
Only the strong survive...
Remember that, Ganta.