[AHOI] I'll relax when this
federal inspection farce
is finally over...
Imbeciles.
That's not to say,
that you're whitewashing
job hasn't been superb.
[TAMAKI] It's easy enough when
one's vision is but a microcosm
of the times as a whole.
A nursery modeled on
a larger truth, if you like.
Lest we forget, Minister:
Good is predicated on
corruption and evil.
Says the sick fuck
who'd see the world bleed.
Now, now...
I'm merely plying my
trade as a liberator...
I provide a much-needed
context to the disenfranchised.
♪ opening song ♪
[NAGI SCREAMS]
[ELITE GUARDS YELL]
[GANTA] Karako!
What have they done?
That isn't him...
He's out of his mind.
[KARAKO]
No, kid... He's just weak.
I tried... I wanted to get him
out of this hell hole...
Because of what he is.
But I'm just as weak.
[ELITE GUARDS YELL]
Do you really think
it's a good idea
to let him kill
the ones on our...
Genkaku...?
[NAGI GROWLS]
So, this is him weak...?
That's why we turn away...
To stay sane.
Damn you...
Why are you still alive?!
No, Ganta! Run!
I'll never forgive
you if you die!
Is that all you got... asshole?!
I don't want
you to save me!
Get out of here!
[GANTA YELLS]
Ganta...! This kind of thing
doesn't even hurt me,
I don't need you to-- Oh, no!
[SHIRO GASPS]
[SHIRO]
You're pathetic...
[BLOWS LANDING]
You're gonna lose.
Do you hear me?!
Stop trying to be all
big and tough and run!
Nagi... Please stop...
This isn't you...
I know it isn't... Listen to me.
You may not think I understand
the kind of darkness
a guy can be driven
to, but I do.
I'd have turned the
Red Man inside out if I could.
But that's not what
it means to be free!
[NAGI]
Freedom is darkness.
My girl... The only light
I had was snuffed out...
All is darkness!
Darkness!
[SHIRO] Ganta!
So that's it...
You've given up...
You just "turned away"...
Out of everybody
I met in this hellhole...
I thought if anyone
would understand...
Maybe I was wrong about you.
But the pain...
The bitter, bitter hatred...
The constant struggle just
to make sense of it all...
Yeah, I've had my share.
Stay down!
[GANTA] I'm nothing...
And if I can find a light...
You sure as hell
ought to be able to!
The light is dead...
All hope has flown...
[BELL CHIMES]
Some part of you
knows that isn't true!
If you'd just open your
eyes, you'd see it...!
Goddamnit, you're the one
who taught me that!
Please, listen to me...
Hope's still here!
[NAGI]
No, I can't...
[NAGI THINKING]
I won't...
Darkness is all...
[BELL CHIMES]
Except you...
[GANTA]
I still have a light...
And believe me, I've done some
pretty horrible things for
someone who dares to hope.
[GANTA]
But... I get it...
I know what's
worth caring about.
And yeah... I'm weak...
But I'm gonna fight this
place with all I got!
That's the least I owe
to the people that I love!
[BELL CHIMES]
[NAGI] You...
[GANTA GRUNTS FEEBLY]
[THUD]
Oh, no! Ganta!
[GANTA THINKING]
This... This isn't anemia...
I know that feeling...
Why am I so... numb...?
Oh, shit...
Oh shit, no... not now!
Yo... Love bird.
[BELL CHIMES]
Karako...
Snap the hell out of it, Nagi!
I need you to be
our leader, dammit!
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[NAGI]
That cheap little bell...
Hard to imagine
the sound of it
taking so long to break
through... huh...?
What have I done...? Oh, no...
[NAGI SOBS]
Look, we can bawl about it
after we get out of this joint.
Yeah.
Heh...
[NAGI GASPS]
[THUD]
How the fuck have
you not yet learned
that I'm a jealous psychopath?
Karako, no!
Karako!
Yeah, spare me
the waterworks, huh...?
'sides, look at it
this way: she's saved.
[GANTA THINKING] Why?!
He just wanted to
see his baby girl!
No...!
Not after everything he's
gone through to help us...!
Damn it, no!
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[GANTA YELLS]
One more... shot.
Please don't!
It'll kill you!
[GANTA SCREAMS]
I blew it.
Hurts like a bitch, huh?
I can take that away.
[KARAKO COUGHS]
Karako!
[KARAKO BREATHES RAPIDLY]
See, I know how to keep
from hittin' the major organs...
Her ribcage is
probably shit now, though.
I'm not the kind of douche who'd
deprive you of the honor...
The woman's in love, after all.
The person who kills her
ought to be you, Owl...
Am I right?
[KARAKO GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Huh...?
Come on, man, death is your
calling card, get on with it!
Embrace yourself!
I'm sorry, friend...
I believe you might've
overestimated me.
To say nothing of death.
Salvation is life...
And mine is right here...
With the people who've
risked everything...
The people I'm
willing to die for.
[KARAKO GASPS]
Tch...
Oh, sweetheart...
Don't do this t'me... Not now.
H-Heh...
I like you so
much better crazy.
The sight of you
spilling blood wholesale...
[GUN FIRES]
[KARAKO GASPS]
[GANTA GASPS]
[NAGI GRUNTS]
[GENKAKU]
That's where the magic was.
Not the silly
piece of shit
who spouts off to me
about "risk" and "life"...
That guy I can do without.
[THUD]
[GUN COCKS]
[GUNFIRE]
[ELITE GUARDS YELL]
[GENKAKU LAUGHS]
Son of a... What in the
world's gotten into you?!
[GENKAKU LAUGHS]
Stop it!!!
[EKISHIN]
Hey, what's new, Red?
You lot still
takin' donations?
[EKISHIN LAUGHS]
[SOUNDS OF IMPACT]
[GENKAKU'S MASTER]
Namu shakyamuni buts...
Another tangle with
the ruffians, I see...
How does a
peace-loving boy like you
get caught up in such things?
[EKISHIN LAUGHS]
[GENKAKU'S MASTER] Violence
begets  violence, my son.
You know this.
Hate has no part of me...
I have compassion for them...
Their suffering is profound...
It cannot be otherwise...
Thus they blindly sow evil.
Huh...?
[YOUNG GENKAKU]
Master...
Can salvation come to
those wrapped in the veil?
Can those who resist
enlightenment
truly be delivered
from illusion?
[LOUD RUMBLING]
Is Death suffering?
And with respect, if so...
How could the Buddha
have known it to be suffering?
[YOUNG GENKAKU]
Farewell...
I'm begging you... Please...
Pull me out... Help me--
[GENKAKU'S MASTER GRUNTS]
Ekishin... Genkaku...
Is anyone injured?
[YOUNG GENKAKU]
Master... I have saved them.
[GENKAKU'S MASTER YELLS]
[YOUNG GENKAKU]
They are free from the veil...
From evil...
Think of it...
The end of suffering.
Death is peace...
Death is silence...
The end of all things...
Stillness of mind...
Of desire...
Of hatred...
Of each soul's delusion...
Death is Rock n' Roll!
Matayoshi?! Harumi!
They wanted to escape,
but they knew not from what...
They thought a view of the sky
would be their salvation.
"What fools these mortals be..."
[BEEPING]
[GANTA GRUNTS]
[SHIRO GASPS]
You okay?
[GENKAKU]
Once it gets a toehold,
the poison spreads
fast... Eh, kid?
How's it feel, knowing this
hole will be your grave?
These are your only options...
Live with the fear...
Embrace the insanity and
all the darkness it brings...
Or shed the yoke of
this world in Death...!
Just think how lucky
you are that I'm here...!
The one who's
gonna set you free!
[HIBANA] I don't
understand what's happening...
I don't want to be
part of this anymore--
Huh...?
So is the cat out of the bag?
Who're you?!
[TOTO]
Invisible Black...
Ow!
Still a bit too delicate,
I suppose... Oh well...
[GANTA THINKING]
Why...?
Why do we have to
die like this...?
Why... Why does it
have to be so ugly?
Why the hell aren't
I strong enough
to do something about it?!
[GANTA YELLS]
Ganta?!
We don't think twice
about putting
a wounded animal
out of its misery;
why are people
any different?
Until I'm saved...
This is what I do.
Releasing my fellows
from the bonds of fear
and oppression...
from the shame of betrayal...
I'm a saint, man!
I erase contempt;
regret, sorrow, insanity...
All the burdens of life!
I just wish someone
would be kind enough
to do as much for me.
Huh...?
[GANTA] Shiro?!
That's right...
Heh... Come on.
[GANTA GRUNTS]
No, let me get this one...
It's my turn to be the hero.
I, owe you an Aceman!
You son of a bitch!
Why you gotta be such a cliché?!
Life hurts, do you think
we don't know that?
But some of us choose
to go on... Regardless...
Some of us don't
have time to die,
'cause people count
on us to survive!
[GUNFIRE]
Yes, that's right, friend.
We're in this together.
I knew you would own
up to your feelings.
[CRUMBLING]
[THUD]
Shiro...!
[KARAKO] Nagi!
He's alive after all that?!
Where are you, kid?
I'm too...
I can't... see you...
[GANTA]
I'm right here.
[NAGI]
Take this... Quickly.
I don't... exactly have
much of a need for it anymore.
[BEEPING]
This is as good
a way to go as any.
No, it's... It's better...
I got to... to see...
you... shine out...
[KARAKO SOBS]
Karako... Thank you...
...for the rain...
It's beautiful...
It feels... like freedom.
You may... just see
a rainbow yet... Someday...
[KARAKO SOBS]
[SHIRO]
The big shiny wheel...
Hi Ganta!
[GANTA]
Shiro... Are you okay?
[SHIRO] Yeah!
So, uh... You, gonna
go outside now...?
That's what you
wanted, isn't it?
Not anymore...
Not if I have to leave you.
So, yeah... That punch...?
I've never felt so horrible.
Except... maybe when
I said all those things...
Aw, c'mon...
I'm much better now.
But you still owe me
a ride on that thing.
Wouldn't be as much
fun all alone, right?
[GANTA] Right...
Huh...?
Ganta...? Something
still hurting you?
[GANTA]
No... No, I'm good.
[GANTA SOBS]
Candy just tastes like shit.
[TAMAKI] Yes, yes... Further
details can wait, I'm sure...
Just know that I depend on you.
[TAMAKI THINKING]
I rather expected
more of the Undertakers.
[TAMAKI SIGHS]
[MAKINA] You're looking
a bit pale there, sir...
Something I should know...?
Have your precious
little birds flown the coop?
[TAMAKI] Whatever are you
implying, my good woman...?
Surely no one under your
jurisdiction cheated the system?
This job was thrust upon
me without my consent.
My predecessor's demise
left me little time
for adjustment.
You're correct to
assume that no one
from my jurisdiction is gone.
5580 and 9061
are both in custody
and have sustained
inexplicable injuries...
But they're safely
under my care.
Upon recovery, they'll
be interrogated as to
their whereabouts over
the last eleven days.
I cannot promise the query
won't be intense...
Do you approve?
You stoop to ask permission?
How exquisitely
coy of you, Makina.
Proceed as you see fit.
Understood.
But I cannot promise the story
they tell won't be intense.
[MAKINA]
Lieutenant.
[KASUGA]
Ma'am...
Would you like me to rub
your shoulders for you?
Have the members
been chosen?
Yes ma'am...
I've gone over the
Promoter's secret list
and one prisoner
in particular
fits the bill
perfectly, I believe.
Excellent...
then we'll act soon.
[TOTO LAUGHS]
[TOTO]
Such a fascinating child
to carry so potent
a Branch of Sin.
Its flavor must be marvelous.
[SHIRO SINGS] ♪ Naughty
birdie's song is made... ♪
♪ by pecking holes in trees... ♪
♪ Willows, cedars,
sycamores... ♪
♪ and proud oaks
reduced to cheese... ♪
♪ woodland gods,
all in a huff, ♪
♪ have forever cursed
your naughty beak... ♪
♪ what it pecks,
it poisons now; ♪
♪ your food, your nest,
even your young... ♪
♪ Your friends
now all fear you... ♪
♪ But your tears ring
clearly through the wood, ♪
♪ even as they
taint the dew... ♪
♪ Such a sad, sad
little birdie... ♪
♪ Maybe one day, this
song will lift the curse ♪
♪ and set you free. ♪
[GANTA] That, song...
It's familiar...
[SHIRO]
'course it is, silly...
It's a song your mommy made up.
[GANTA] It's pretty
and all, but...
Could you stop?
[SHIRO] Huh...?
Sorry...
It's just that...
Last time I heard it
all my friends got killed.
[SHIRO]
That's awful.
It's weird the Red Man
would sing it...
I dunno... Maybe I'm
just over-thinkin' it.
♪ closing song ♪