[YURI] I still
can't believe it, Kirill.
[MAXINE] I don't think any
of us expected that.
I wouldn't've either. Crazy.
But, like, you seem
pretty chill about it all.
[KIRILL]
Huh? It's not a big deal.
I would've been more
shocked if Milla'd
been dressed like
a man, honestly.
It's a non-issue.
Anyway, on some level it all
feels like a dream, you know?
Yeah. I guess that makes sense.
[DEANA]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what?!
So... Uh...
It might be kinda rude
to ask you this, but...
Why do you do it?
If you know it's rude,
save your breath, dumbass!
Darn tootin'!
Milla's life choices aren't
anybody else's business!
[APPLE]
Mm...
It's okay.
I've never been averse
to talking about it.
About what?
Did I miss somethin', or--?
Well... I--
Lady stuff. Bring us the check.
We're leaving.
Uh. Okay.
[NARRATOR]
Let me explain.
Right after this, Deana gave
everyone strict instructions,
"Don't tell Delick, or Derick"
and then she sent
them on their way.
I mean, I almost feel
sorry for the guy!
He's got what he thinks is this
cute new female hire, right?
But, Milla's really a cute male
hire in women's clothes.
Why lie, though?
Milla has no reason to hide.
[DEANA]
It's more fun this way.
I just love a little
dramatic irony, don't you?
That's Classic Deana.
[DEANA]
Hey, Buzz-Cut!
You'd better make damn sure Doug
knows not to spill the beans!
Uh, okay. Wait.
Where is he, anyway?
Out.
I think I heard that he's
taking another half-day.
Huh. More laundry?
[YURI] No. He said something
important came up.
[KIRILL]
Huh...
[DOUG] I just remembered
it's your birthday.
Sorry I'd forgotten.
Damn. I can't believe
it's been eight years.
Time does fly.
[liquid pours]
[PAUL humming]
[DOUG]
How much for a pack of smokes?
Hello, there, "No-scale Paul."
I'm sorry, what?
You must have the
wrong guy, my friend.
Because I don't know anybody
with that dumb name.
Huh?
Doug!
You should've said
you were coming!
I like knowing when old
friends are stopping by.
[DOUG]
Just passing through on a whim.
[PAUL]
Visiting that grave again?
Your old partner, right?
That's right.
[PAUL] It's been a long time
since I saw you here.
[DOUG] You seem to be staying
on the right side of the law.
I'm happy to see that.
I always liked you.
[PAUL] Ah, come on,
stop blowin' smoke, man.
Some of my old buddies were
freaking out about my choice.
I don't know if you've
gotten wind or not,
but word on the street is
Good-looking Joe is back.
[DOUG grunts]
[TRAVIS]
That corpse they found
in the fire was positively
IDd as Zabel.
So, we can all rest easy there.
Forensics got a match
from his dental records.
That was the only thing
left for them to go on.
We suspect a revenge
hit by A's buddies,
but, there are other
theories floating around.
Like Bamboo Man.
Or, B, trying to
shut old Zabel up.
We're still trying
to find the source
of Bamboo Man's freakish powers.
Doctor Apple's hard at work,
attempting to improve
the Shield Coat,
and developing more
effective weapons
against this type of threat.
Everybody stay sharp out there.
We can't afford mistakes now.
You're dismissed.
[GROUP]
Yes, sir!
[KIRILL]
Do you think...
...the theories about Bamboo
Man killing Zabel are true?
[DOUG] I think it's not
your problem to solve.
[KIRILL]
I'm just curious.
[DOUG]
He was on death row, anyway.
A dead man walking. It just
went down differently.
How can you be so
callous, though?
I just don't get too invested.
That's the trick to keeping
your head out here.
[KIRILL gasping]
My first partner passed away.
Still haunts me.
Hey, Doug.
You wanna grab a drink
with me tonight?
I can't.
I've got this thing
that I have to go to.
For real? That's unusual.
I know. Just meeting
my old boss, no biggie.
[KIRILL]
I see.
[MAXINE]
Oh. To tell you the truth,
I know virtually nothing
about Doug's past.
He's not the type to go around
talking about himself, y'know?
Doug's former partner?
Do you mean...
This guy?
[KIRILL]
No, not you. A different one.
So, then, you?
[sighs]
[MORGAN] You wanna know about
your partner's old partner?
Seems weird to be
asking me about it.
But... If you got the money,
I got the info, man.
[KIRILL]
Thanks. I'm all ears.
[ZABEL]
I'm very pleased with it, B.
It seems almost as secure
as the prison, in fact.
[BAMBOO MAN]
Thank you, sir.
The police have
been cracking down
a lot harder than usual lately.
Because of that, I felt
the need to fortify
the organization in
every way possible.
[ZABEL] And that's where
these gentlemen come in.
Without your eye on the matter,
there's no way we'd be
able to handle them all.
I remember him.
Still as handsome as ever, huh?
Good-Looking Joe.
[DENNIS]
Joe? You don't mean, that Joe.
Pat Morino's--
I do. I got the intel from Paul.
If you have something,
Dennis, I need it.
Sorry.
Haven't heard
anything about that.
Since I retired, I've tried
to stay out of it all.
I understand.
Well, if you do hear something,
make sure I'm the
first one who knows.
Let it go, Doug.
Nothing good can come
of this, not with that guy.
Forget about Pat.
Move on with your life.
[KIRILL] Doug started acting
weird around then.
Seemed edgier than usual.
Good-lookin' Joe?
I ain't heard of nobody
who goes by that.
Oh, yeah?
Word is he's makin' a comeback.
Heh. Even if I knew,
why would I tell you, pig?
[PRISONER 7A grunts]
I hate games. Talk.
Come on!
He already confessed to the
charges, Doug, let him go!
Doug!
[KIRILL] It wasn't like
him to become obsessed
with a case like this.
He broke his own rule and
got emotionally invested.
[KIRILL] Listen. You've been
acting weird lately.
What's going on?
Who is this Good-looking
Joe guy to you, anyway?
Workday's done. I'm outta here.
[JOE] So, you're sayin' the cops
are sniffing around after me?
[CHIEF HENCHMAN 7A]
Yeah. Some guy with SEVEN-O.
Name's Doug Billingham,
apparently.
[JOE]
Huh. Doesn't ring a bell.
Is that all you've got on him?
[CHIEF HENCHMAN 7A] I heard
he used to be a detective
with Precinct Three.
[JOE]
Ah, now, that's more like it.
Dennis's old unit, I believe.
That brings me right back.
[DOUG]
If you happen to hear anything,
contact me immediately.
[KIRILL]
Even on his days off,
Doug would spend
all his time searching
for clues about this Joe.
So far,
I'd gathered that
Joe was a gangster
who had made a name
for himself in the area.
Back before Esperanza
had become what it is now.
I could only imagine why Doug
had developed such tunnel
vision about it all.
What's with you?
You've been so secretive.
It bothers me.
Look, don't worry.
I won't cause you
any trouble, got it?
[KIRILL] But you've become
obsessed, Doug!
Is it because
Pat Morino's involved?
[DOUG]
Where'd you hear that name?
[KIRILL] You sure you've
got the right info?
Yeah. Nobody had heard anything
about his coworkers or
other partners dying.
The only thing I did hear,
is that he was particularly fond
of a certain information broker,
and that was the only
person close to him
who ended up getting offed.
Who is this Pat Morino?
Someone close to you?
[DOUG]
Yeah.
[KIRILL]
I thought so.
You're not trying to get
revenge for that, are you?
Do you think I'm
that old-fashioned?
Don't worry.
[TRAVIS] Pat Morino, huh?
So... What did he say?
[KIRILL]
Uh. Come on. You know Doug.
He didn't really say anything.
Okay. Then I suppose I
shouldn't say a word, either.
[JOE] No doubt you've heard
all the rumors, right?
About this SEVEN-O
detective who's been
asking about me all over town?
I don't know anything about him,
so I've been choosing
to ignore it.
But then I found out someone's
been meeting with him,
giving him information on me.
[PAUL]
P-Please!
I didn't mean to tell him!
[JOE]
Oh, I know that, Paul.
We're friends.
Why would you betray me?
Uh. Hey, uh. Lemme
ask you something.
Ever heard of a Pat Morino?
[JOE]
I haven't, who's that?
Man, I wish I knew.
But, still. If Doug is
out lookin' for you--
that's the reason.
[JOE]
Huh.
[PAUL] Look, if you
promise not to hurt me,
I'll tell you everything I know.
Even though I got out of this
ugly scene a long time ago, man.
[JOE]
Yes, I heard that.
Got a kid now and everything.
So, you'd sell out the
detective who saved your life
to protect your little family?
[CHIEF HENCHMAN 7A]
Stay still!
Uh. No! Wait! Please don't!
I'll talk!
[JOE]
You're a very bad man, Paul.
[DENNIS] Listen, why not
back off for a while?
Let 'em cool off--
they're out for blood.
I just can't.
I understand how you feel,
but nothing you do is going to
bring Pat back from the grave.
And to be fair,
there's no proof
Good-looking Joe
had anything to do
with Pat's death.
Which is why I'm investigating.
Your co-workers are
going to get hurt, Doug.
We're all detectives.
That's an occupational hazard.
[JOE] One of the dealers on my
turf has been apprehended.
He caught a charge.
[CHIEF HENCHMAN 7A]
No, another one?
Yeah.
It's that Doug Billingham guy.
[ringing]
[JOE] Hey there, Doug
Billingham, right?
You on duty today?
[DOUG]
Joe?
[JOE]
I'm quite pleased to see
you're keeping yourself
busy out there.
[DOUG]
You're right, very busy.
So, I gotta go, sorry. Bye, now.
[JOE]
Wait, Doug.
I think there may be a
slight misunderstanding
between the two of us.
I'm rather busy, too, and would
hate to create more work
for myself than necessary.
Why don't you and I meet
for a little chat?
[DOUG] I don't think we have
anything to discuss.
Doug says he'll be right over.
[DOUG]
Huh?
[DENNIS] Don't, Doug!
It's a trap, stay away!
[DOUG gasps]
[JOE] I think you
recognize that voice.
Fine.
How many men have you got?
[JOE]
Huh?
[DOUG] Better bring
as many as you can.
That way I can
claim self-defense
without any questions.
[KIRILL] You want me to
take over your shift?
That's rare.
Yeah, well.
There's somewhere I gotta be.
Sounds like somebody's
got himself
a hot lead on Good-Looking Joe.
[KIRILL gasps]
Just forget your
revenge, Doug. Please.
I can't turn down
this invitation.
[KIRILL] Well, what are you
doing bringing this with you?
Mind your business.
I've got permission to carry
that when I'm off-duty.
That's not even what
I'm talking about.
[KIRILL]
Crap! What the--?
[DOUG] Some kind of tranquilizer
Doctor Apple developed.
Nighty-night.
[crash]
It's almost over, old friend.
Gotta borrow this for a bit.
[KIRILL]
Doug...
[DOUG] Take me to Joe,
don't ask questions.
[gasps]
[TRAVIS] Wait, wait, wait.
He's out for revenge?
[KIRILL]
Yeah, I'm positive now!
Why didn't you try to stop him?
Well, I, uh. I didn't realize
things had already
progressed to that point.
There's a chance he's
gonna murder someone!
So, what, then?
Should I have told Doug to
drop the case altogether?
I don't know.
[TRAVIS] Do you have proof
it's all about revenge?
Who would even make that call?
Is it me? Or you, perhaps?
[TRAVIS] I trust the morality
of all my detectives.
Didn't you hear
what I just said?
[KIRILL]
Oh, shut up!
I can't believe I almost let you
talk me out of following him!
[JOE]
Welcome, good sir.
What'd you do with Dennis?
[JOE] Now, drop the weapon and
put your hands behind your head.
[clattering]
[DENNIS grunts]
What's the matter?
You can go.
[JOE]
Oh, I almost forgot.
Dennis is a regular.
Shows up like clockwork.
How do you think
I was able to find out
everything there was to know
about you and your friend,
No-scale Paul?
Heh. It's so ironic.
Your old boss is a
textbook drug addict.
[DENNIS]
Please forgive me, Doug.
Sure. I should've picked
up on the signs sooner.
[JOE] Now, let's talk about you,
Doug Billingham.
First of all,
I've been hearing you've got it
out for me because I killed
an information broker by
the name of Pat Morino.
I feel bad.
Because I don't have the
faintest clue who that is.
Would you be a pal and tell me?
[KIRILL]
A shoe shiner?
It's true.
Pat shined shoes as a cover,
but made actual money
selling information.
Eight years ago, when Doug
was a brand-new detective,
Esperanza was much more
violent than they are now,
if you can believe that.
Their members were maniacs.
Always after each other's
throats like a bunch of animals.
One day, Pat was shining
shoes, as usual.
And met an untimely
and very tragic end.
Got riddled with bullets.
Thirteen of them in all.
And this Good-looking
Joe was responsible?
[TRAVIS] There was never
any proof found of that.
Joe disappeared shortly after,
dropped right off the map.
That's part of Doug's
obsession with Esperanza.
He wants to find his
proof and act on it.
[JOE] Oh, I remember it now!
The whole story!
All I want to know is this:
Why'd you kill Pat?
[JOE]
Huh?
[DOUG] There was no
justifiable reason for it.
[JOE]
The shoe polish job.
I hate when people use the wrong
color when they polish my shoes!
I hope you rot in hell.
Huh?
You'd kill for that?
You bastard. You murdered
an innocent kid over shoes?
[TRAVIS]
Pat Morino. Short for Patricia.
At the time, she was
a 12-year-old girl.
[JOE]
She would be, what?
Twenty now? Come on.
Her life was going
nowhere anyway.
It was a mercy, don't you agree?
Doug Billingham.
I'm relieved to finally meet
you face-to-face, Joe.
You're even more
despicable than I thought.
[JOE] Well, I think that's
enough talk for one evening.
[snaps]
[KIRILL]
How awful. You mean, this guy
just murdered a 12-year-old
orphan in cold blood?
That's the sad truth.
It's what started it all.
Doug's hatred of poverty
and the class system.
At least, that's what I think.
[DOUG] Strength in numbers
doesn't apply here.
You're going to have to
outsmart me to survive.
[JOE]
Remember, you requested them.
It's a little trick I've learned
over the past eight years.
Oh, is this the little
"trick" you mentioned?
I must say, I'm disappointed.
A Lady Joker, eh?
Ooh, and with
hollow points, too.
[JOE chuckles]
I do love the juxtaposition
of a cute little gun loaded
with such a brutal
kind of bullet.
[TRAVIS]
You know. Doug never bought
a shred of information
from Pat over the years.
He wanted her to get out.
To drop the business because
of the danger it put her in.
He really cared about that kid.
But she refused to
heed his advice.
So Doug settled for
the next best thing.
He gave her a gun, so she
could protect herself.
[KIRILL]
Doug bought a child a gun?
[TRAVIS] Yeah. He slipped
her a Lady Joker one day,
in case she ran into trouble.
You don't know how
predictable you are.
I knew a coward would
make this choice.
Goodbye, Doug.
Nope, I win.
Uh?
[DOUG]
I loaded it with dummies.
Except the fourth one,
which was a flash bullet.
[KIRILL] So, she refused
to take the gun? How odd.
Indeed. That's what I heard.
[KIRILL]
But why?
[TRAVIS] Who knows?
That part is anyone's guess.
No, Doug.
A policeman isn't supposed
to break the rules.
[DOUG grunts]
[TRAVIS]
Her death changed Doug forever.
[TRAVIS] Doug's penchant
for following rules
and regulations on
every job stems from it.
I guess he thought
he could minimize
any future pain that way.
But I'm no therapist.
[JOE whimpers]
[DOUG] Anyone who banks on
their cronies protecting them
will inevitably let
their guard down.
Cowards like you
are all the same.
You think using all
the best weapons
will make up for your weakness.
Wait! Let's talk!
I'm sure we can
work something out!
You're a detective, right?
That's true. I am.
Now, I have some good news
and bad news for you, Joe.
Which do you want first?
The good news is I can
blow your head off
and claim self-defense without
any pesky questions.
Hey! What? You lied!
That's only good news for you,
it's all bad for me!
Yeah, you're right.
And that brings me
to the bad news.
You're gonna die without anyone
hearing you complain about it.
Except me, and I don't care.
[JOE gasping]
Hey!
[DOUG] Tell Patricia sorry
in your next life,
Good-looking Joe.
[gunshot]
[gasps]
Did you...?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just made some
arrests, that's all.
[KIRILL]
It misfired?
[DOUG]
Yeah, a bad cylinder.
That thing's been sitting
on a shelf too long.
And it's not much
more than a toy.
[KIRILL]
I see.
Revenge is old-fashioned,
remember?
Damn straight!
Move! That as fast
as you can walk?
[TRAVIS]
Paul woke up a little while ago.
Just got off the phone
with the hospital.
That's good news.
Thanks for sharing.
I am curious, though, Doug.
That gun.
You were sure it
was going to misfire
when you pulled the
trigger, weren't you?
Well, uh...
[KIRILL]
Interesting.
Guess this means
your "old partner"
didn't really want
revenge after all.
That's why the gun misfired.
She had to stop it.
[gasps]
Yes.
I knew it.
[TRAVIS]
Right!
All's well that
ends well, folks!
My partner set me straight.
He told me
a young girl would prefer
something like this.
No more guns or whiskey.
[DOUG]
You know something?
I imagine that you two
would've been good friends.
[NARRATOR] An incident breaks
out at a local high school,
and Max's mysterious
past is revealed!
Guess we'll find out
how little Maxine
became the Max we know and love!
Next time, on Double Decker !
Episode Eight: "Dancing!
Academy Investigation!"
Hey! No dancing in
the meeting room!
Take the party outside!