[NARRATOR] SEVEN-O's got some
new gadgets, friends!
Number one!
With these, you can speed down
even the most narrow,
cluttered roads!
Jet roller skates!
Number two!
Equipped with powerful rockets,
it's sure to come in handy
at some point!
Jet pack!
Number three!
Wanna see what
your partner sees?
Now you can!
New function. View Jack!
[NARRATOR]
That last one?
It's right out of every
adolescent boy's wildest dreams.
Sick new items, man!
Those are all super badass!
Go, Apple!
[laughs] Thanks, but I insist
you call me, "Doctor."
Really nice work, Apple!
[APPLE laughs]
What'd I just say?
You might win a science
fair with these,
but none of 'em will help us
to solve a damn thing,
Apple Bieber.
It's "Doctor"!
So, can we talk about
this weird new function
you put into the eye system?
It's called the view jack.
Sure, that.
You could use it to spy
on us while we're changing.
[APPLE gasps]
Uh...
[KAY gasps]
No, I would never!
You've got it all wrong here!
Its primary function
is sharing information,
particularly on
Overdrive targets.
[DEANA]
Aw, hell, no!
Okay, fine.
I'll adjust it, then!
I said hell no, Apple.
Doug! Help me out, please!
[DOUG] I mean, this stuff
is cool, and all,
but I do see the
ladies' point here.
Plus, it's hard to say
if we'd use any of this.
[APPLE groans]
[NARRATOR]
That's right!
This is just your typical,
run-of-the-mill cop show
about good detectives
haunting a beat, so.
If you want cool tech,
you'd better look elsewhere!
Hey. Twavis says
he needs you all
to come see him, quick.
[GROUP]
Hm?
Something about a kidnapping.
[NARRATOR]
Yes, she did just say, "Twavis!"
[TRAVIS] This victim is a young
woman named Sarah Dorman.
The daughter of William Dorman,
the leading mayoral candidate.
That is unfortunate, but what's
it got to do with us?
Yeah. Kidnapping cases are
outside our jurisdiction.
[door creaks]
[COOPER]
Indeed, allow me to explain.
Whoa! Who's that?
You seriously don't know?
What a dumbass!
This is Brian Cooper.
Our Military Secretary.
[KIRILL gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Yep. You folks are smart,
so I'm sure you remember that,
despite being a police
organization first,
SEVEN-O is also under
military jurisdiction!
[COOPER]
The criminals gave us a clue
when they sent us
their ransom demand.
They identified themselves
as Esperanza.
[KIRILL gasping]
[DOUG]
"Ransom demand"?
So, that means this
is just a cash grab.
[COOPER] Your assessment
is likely correct.
But, in light of the upcoming
mayoral elections,
we need to be open to the idea
that Dorman's political rivals
could also be involved.
And, considering the fact that
we're going up against
Esperanza, we can't
afford to take chances.
We've got to be ready
for anything.
[DOUG]
Understood, sir.
So, we should treat this
as a direct case, then?
[KIRILL]
Hey, what's a direct case?
[KAY]
It's the term for a case
that comes directly
from the military.
[COOPER] Yes, but there's
a bit more to this one.
[TRAVIS]
What else should we know?
Please save my daughter,
I beg you!
Save my dear Sarah! Please!
I don't even care if the media
says I'm weak for negotiating
with kidnappers! Let them!
Just save her!
[COOPER]
And Dorman, well...
He's an old friend
of the family.
[DOUG]
Say no more, sir. We're on it.
So, is there a plan
in place yet?
[TRAVIS] There's a great deal
more risk involved than usual.
Mister Dorman has insisted upon
handing over the ransom himself.
You'll be nearby, surveying.
And, in the event that
things don't go as planned,
you'll be there for backup.
Doug, you're the team leader.
Mr. Dorman will be
wearing a radio,
but for security reasons, he
won't have his own receiver.
Your priority here is the
victim's safety, above all else.
And don't worry about
apprehending the suspects.
[phone rings]
There he goes. Doug? Follow?
[DOUG]
Yeah. Be careful, you two.
[siren blares]
[KIRILL gasps]
[KAY] He's headed
towards the river now.
[DEANA]
Well, shit.
What's the matter?
[DEANA]
There's a fire.
[sirens blare]
[KIRILL growls]
Dammit. Problem here, too.
We'll have to take
the long way around.
[DOUG]
Roger that. I'll tail him alone.
[DEANA]
Damn! I lost my view.
Not good. They found
the transmitter.
[ALL gasp]
[DOUG] It's looking bad.
They're onto us, no doubt.
I'm gonna have to handle
this one by myself!
[DORMAN] You give me back
my daughter, now!
[THUG 09B groans]
[THUG 09A groans]
Are you okay, sir?
[DEANA]
Hey, where did they go?
[BOTH gasp]
Understood. I'll ask for
a cordon on the main roads.
Let's hope they're not
out of the ward yet.
Target is confirmed
on the run...
Do you suspect that
the fire was arson?
Yes. An attempt to sabotage
our investigation.
A clever one, too.
They knew firefighters would
need to gather near the river.
[DORMAN] Hey, this wasn't
part of the deal!
SEVEN-O was supposed to
botch the investigation.
Then I'd look like a hero
when I rescued my
daughter all by myself!
It was the plan
we all agreed upon!
That way, I'd be sure to win
the election and the current
mayor's drug policies
would go out the window.
It was win-win!
So, what'd I miss?
[ZABEL]
The plan changed.
We have a higher priority
to address now.
[DORMAN]
Who are you? I don't like this.
[ZABEL]
I have a little message for you
to pass along to your friends.
I don't know who you are,
but no part of the plan
included kidnapping a cop!
Cooper's a family friend!
What the hell are we
supposed to do
if something happens
to the officer, huh?
[ZABEL]
Heh.
Oh, no. Did you kill him?
[DORMAN groans]
[ZABEL] I'm afraid the matter
is none of your business.
Sorry. You will keep
your promise, though.
You're going to do everything we
tell you to, with no exceptions.
We're in this together now.
Even if you wanted out,
there's no turning back.
But, is my daughter safe?
[ZABEL] I'll release her without
a scratch, as promised.
The boss decided in
the pen that he wouldn't
be killin' kids no more.
Good news for you.
[THUG 09A] Yeah, but the bad
news is he shows no mercy
to people who waste
perfectly good food.
Daddy fought bravely
to rescue his poor,
innocent daughter
from the bad guys.
That's the story you want
the papers to run, right?
[APPLE sighs]
Just like I thought, no luck.
These cameras are positioned
to monitor the river.
Can't expect much.
Can we check any
of the other feeds?
They're in a stolen vehicle.
The license plates aren't
gonna tell us a damn thing.
Poor Doug.
If he doesn't make it...
Don't even think that!
Buzz-Cut. You can't just leave.
That's right, we're on standby.
Kirill!
Dammit, Doug!
I'm the one who's supposed
to get caught! Ya jerk!
[DEANA] How could those lowlifes
have known about our plan?
What the hell is going on here?
Do you think they were
listening in on our messages?
There's no possible way.
I used my own personal brand
of encryption on them.
It's pretty much infallible.
Maybe your ego
is to blame, then.
What if you're wrong, and
they broke the encryption?
The radio output is so low
the signal's barely detectible!
The technology that
amplifies the receiver--
I'm the only person
who knows how to-- Uh!
[door opens]
[MAXINE]
Deana. Kay. Listen.
[beeping]
[DEANA] Buzz-Cut, you read?
Better come back.
We found Dorman's daughter.
[gasps]
[MAXINE]
When we located the victim,
she was able to give
the exact location
of the kidnappers' hideout.
Dorman was found soon after,
unconscious in a seedy
hotel room in the area.
Did they find Doug yet?
The room was otherwise empty.
Nobody in there but Dorman.
So, they're keeping
Doug somewhere else.
All right. Are we positive
we can trust this info?
[MAXINE]
Yes. No doubt in my mind, sir.
The daughter gave us some
additional intel, as well.
Something that her dad picked
up from one of the kidnappers.
[DORMAN]
You must've been so scared.
I'm sorry... Sarah.
But you're strong,
you'll be fine.
Pass along a message from me.
Can you do that?
"Sergeant Doug Billingham
isn't dead, yet."
I wanted to say thank you
for all your help
when we last met, Doug.
I would be dead
if it weren't for you,
and I will never forget that.
But why would they take Doug?
If the kidnapping
was truly a ploy
then maybe
the kidnappers' real aim
was to take an
investigator hostage.
[ALL gasp]
For revenge?
No, sir.
As evil as they are,
they're not stupid.
[gasps] For information?
[COOPER] Yes. That's more
the more likely scenario.
I get it.
So that's what you've
been after all along?
[splash]
[muffled groans]
[COOPER] We can safely
assume that Esperanza
kidnapped one of your comrades--
to torture him for
classified information.
And my best guess?
They want any intelligence
he can provide regarding
your Anti-AMS bullets.
We already know quite a lot.
The five Overdrive antidote
drugs, for example.
However, we need your help
with some of the particulars,
proper dosages and such.
All of the drugs
are extremely potent.
Some are even fatal in
the wrong quantities.
So, you see the tangle
that we're in?
We need you to tell us
the appropriate formulas,
and the order of operations,
if you don't mind.
And I was hoping you might
be willing to tell me how
this lovely little
device functions?
It's such a mystery to me.
That sounds just like something
Esperanza would do.
I know how to find Doug!
I've got a great idea!
[gasps]
Using the view jack?
Yes.
I made a modification
to the radio program
that expanded
the receiver range.
Way to outdo yourself, Apple!
Okay. There!
[KIRILL]
Zabel. But how?
[DOUG]
I get it now... Zabel.
[ZABEL] Hm? Have you decided
to cooperate, then?
[DOUG]
It's reversed.
The code works backwards.
Reverse alphabetical order.
You've always been the boss.
And what if I have?
[DOUG] Then all I have
to do is take you out
and Esperanza's finished.
[FEMALE THUG 9A]
Boss. Everything's ready to go.
Can't ID the building.
There aren't enough visual
markers to tell much.
Well, if Doug knew,
maybe he could give us
some clues as to
his whereabouts.
Don't worry, he knows
we're watching along.
I modified it,
to deter peeping toms.
[DOUG groans]
[ZABEL]
If you don't talk, you'll die.
But you knew that.
I won't die as easily
as you might think.
'Cause I've finally
found a way forward.
[APPLE]
What is that?
It's a map of
the parking garage.
I'll go run a search for all
garages with that layout.
Come on.
We need to act fast.
Yeah. Doug will never let
these guys break him.
Somehow I could sense that.
He would rather die
than give in!
[ZABEL] Hm... Looks like
he won't be talking,
no matter what atrocities
we subject him to.
Unless something were to happen
that altered his mind
as well as his body.
Perhaps then he'll sing
just like a nightingale.
They're gonna dose
him with Anthem!
Unfortunately, that does seem
to be the plan of attack.
I wish we could tell Doug
what we're up to.
Beyond just letting him know
we're able to watch this.
Wait, I think I
figured something out!
We can send him
whatever message we want!
[GROUP]
Hm?
[ZABEL]
The choice is yours, Billingham.
[THUG 09B]
Uh? What do we do?
[THUG 09A]
I don't wanna...
[KAY]
We can use Morse code.
Doug will notice the on
and off indicator flashing!
[DOUG gasps]
SEVEN-O...
[KIRILL]
What are you telling him?
It's just a simple message
to get his attention.
Hopefully, he'll catch on
fast to what we're doing.
I found out where
they're holding him.
It's the parking structure
on Simpson Drive.
I'll call in a military
special forces unit for back-up.
We'll send in a chopper to
retrieve him from above.
A helicopter's way too risky!
Well, can you think of a faster
way to get to him, then?
[gasps] Doug is using Morse
code to respond!
What? How?
Blinking in rhythm.
He's badly injured
from electric shock, but...
Oh, Doug.
Tell us.
"I'm waiting. Out."
Hey, Boss. I've got an idea.
I approve. Let's do it.
[gasps]
Extralegal measures approved.
The Lisvalletta military shall
assume full responsibility.
Do whatever it takes, team!
Just get out there and
bring Doug back safely!
[ALL]
Roger!
[TRAVIS]
Sophie will continue to monitor
Doug and Buzz-Cuts'
fields of vision.
Buzz-Cut's on the move,
and he'll lead us
to Doug's location.
Pink and Rookie,
you're to provide support
from the rear.
Boxer and Robot,
you'll secure the exit route
so, we can move him out
fast once we've got him.
Buzz-Cut, you're going right
into the belly of the beast
to do whatever you can to
distract the enemy from within.
Then you'll head straight to the
seventh floor and rescue Doug.
We'll call it Operation Beehive!
[TRAVIS]
The team leader is... Buzz-Cut!
[exhales]
[KIRILL] I'll save you,
Doug, no matter what!
The Double Decker system.
It's required of all of you.
You work with a partner at
all times for good reason.
Namely, to keep
your partner alive--
that is your number
one responsibility.
I'm counting on you!
[KIRILL]
Yeah. You can count on me!
Failure is not
an option here, Buzz-Cut.
Are you ready for this?
Don't think, Kirill.
Feel so good. Boo-yah!
[COOPER]
Hm?
It's just a little
good luck charm.
[THUG 09B]
Aw, man.
Is this gonna
kill him, you think?
Guess we'll see.
Hey! C'mon!
If he's not gonna talk,
we don't have a choice!
Yeah, and when he
turns into a monster,
then we can just shoot him dead.
Hold on.
Hm? Have you decided to talk?
[DOUG]
Give me... ten seconds.
--Huh?
--Hm?
Countdown initiated. Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six... Five...
--Leave it to me.
--Four...
--Time to stir up the beehive.
--Three... Two...
--Dance for me, little bees!
--One...
Go!
What was that?
[THUGS groaning]
[THUG 09B]
What the hell?!
[THUGS yelp]
A car just exploded?
[THUG 09A]
Shit!
[THUG 09B]
You're comin' with us!
What? No more Anthem?
[THUG 09A]
Just shut up and walk!
Sophie. Where's Doug now?
Kirill. They're taking him
to the top floor!
[KAY]
Confirmed hit!
Right. Kay. Next!
Yes! Location's at six o'clock.
Distance is 180.
Good girl.
I'll give you some
nice doggie treats later.
Just as I thought they would.
The target is
heading up to the roof.
Boxer, Robot, you're up!
[MAXINE, YURI]
Roger!
Kirill, you'd better hurry!
[KIRILL] I can't go
much faster than I am!
[SOPHIE] But the enemy's on
the verge of figuring it out!
Oh! Now the lady's pointing
a gun right at him!
Oh! But now Doug's got the gun!
Oh! Oh! Behind you! Oh!
"Oh," doesn't tell me
a damn thing, Sophie!
Oh! Sorry! Oh!
Uh, um. He just jumped off!
[KIRILL]
Huh?!
[SOPHIE]
Get ready to rendezvous!
"Rendezvous"?!
[gasps]
[DOUG gasping]
Do I have to ride up here?
Just be quiet and stay on me!
[DOUG]
What do we do now?
[KIRILL]
We do... this!
[DOUG grunting]
[KIRILL] Hang on tight now,
Doug! Let's go!
[yells]
[gasping]
[KIRILL]
Hey! Stay still! Damn it!
So close!
[gasping]
I think that this
crazy plan worked. Maybe?
Wow, Kay, you sound
so... confident.
[YURI]
Are you okay down there?
Yeah. I'm all right.
But I don't think
I can move anymore.
You two are model Double
Deckers, you know that?
This looks like a Triple Decker.
Hey! Not everyone
can breathe right now!
[DOUG] Not much longer.
You've got this.
[KIRILL] What if I die
before we get there?!
[KAY] Mr. Dorman confessed
to his involvement.
He thought being a hero would
help him win the election.
His genius idea
was to stage
the fake kidnapping
so he would come out
looking like a rock star.
[TRAVIS] Yep. I figured it was
something along those lines.
So, uh.
We caused lots of
property damage.
Are we gonna have
to answer for that?
Of course not. Trust me.
Leave it to yours truly.
Travis, you're so cool!
[TRAVIS]
The Lisvalletta military
shall assume full
responsibility!
Whelp. I guess
it all worked out.
Hey, uh. I was a big
help, you guys.
Yeah. You did stellar
work... Doctor Apple.
Dammit, call me Doctor A--
But now, will you please
take off that view jack crap?
Just because it came in handy
this time doesn't make it okay!
Fine. I'll take it off.
Wait. Is Kirill coming into
the office today, or what?
[MAXINE] Nah, he's off.
He went to visit Doug.
[KIRILL] "You don't need
to thank me, buddy.
I just did what any
partner would've."
Yep. That's right.
Gotta look out for
your Double Decker.
Uh!
Ah. Hello, there.
I dropped by to offer Sergeant
Billingham an apology.
I put his life in jeopardy,
and I want him to know
I'll never forget that.
You're kind, but Doug would
never think twice about it.
[COOPER] I'm impressed with
how brave you all are.
Nah. I'm nothing special.
Heh. Bye!
By the way.
That little good luck
charm of yours.
Where did you say
you heard it, again?
Huh?
[COOPER] "Don't think.
Feel so good." Wasn't that it?
Oh. That. Right.
It's just a little motto
my grandfather
taught me before
he passed away.
Though, to be honest, I'm not
sure those are the exact words.
I forget.
I see. Well,
it's still good advice.
My grandpa would've
loved to hear you say that.
See ya, sir!
[door creaks]
[DOUG]
Thank you, Constable Vrubel.
You don't need to
thank me, buddy.
I just did what any par--
You're officially my hero now.
[KIRILL gasping]
If the roles had been reversed,
I'm not so sure I would have
done the same for you.
So, I feel especially grateful.
[KIRILL]
Huh?
That's right! Doug!
Why didn't you come save me
when I was in danger?!
[DOUG]
Hm? Well, I--
I just said that's why
I'm so grateful to you.
[KIRILL] That doesn't
make it better, though!
[COOPER]
"Prometheus's fire
is there when you
don't think, feel so.
Good gifts and blessings
shall be given to you then."
How'd he know it?
Precious few have
heard Nikai's prayer.
[NARRATOR] The team succeeded
in rescuing Doug.
But next time, something
unexpected happens!
Or maybe it doesn't!
That's right!
With love, boxes of chocolates,
and Double Decker,
you never know
what you're gonna get!
Next time, episode ten:
"Failed Detective, but Pure!"
Who cares if I fail?
I'm untarnished!