[SHOW HOST]
A few days ago, on the 27th,
a body was found in the
burned-out remnants of a house
in the Strummer District,
located in Sileoterra.
A suspect has been
arrested for arson...
[KIRILL]
Hey, man.
It's been five whole days now.
You don't think these guys
could have figured us out
and skipped town when we
weren't looking, do you?
It seems weird that
a wanted pack mule
would use such a conspicuous
place as his hideout,
you know what I mean?
As for this "testimony,"
it came from P and Q,
just a couple of nobodies.
We should forget it
and go in after this guy.
[DOUG]
Three minutes.
Thanks a lot, Doug.
[DOUG] This boring stuff
always leads us to the mark.
We just have to be patient
and let it play out.
You're so type A it's funny.
[DOUG] Stakeouts are
a basic part of police work.
But it has been five
days, and nothing.
You might be right about this.
I guess we had better head out.
[SOPHIE]
This is SEVEN-O HQ.
Come in, officers. You read me?
[KIRILL]
Oh, right, right.
Hey, Kirill speaking.
Yeah, he's right here. Dougie.
[DOUG] Hm? A request
for back up? For real?
[TRAVIS]
Yeah, from the local PD.
There's a disturbance down at
Casino Victoria in Marinaurben.
Some drunk causing a scene.
[DOUG] Hm? So, what's
that got to do with us?
[TRAVIS]
I think it's about something
the guy keeps screaming.
"I'm a syndicate boss!",
or something along those lines.
And he means Esperanza?
[TRAVIS] Well, we don't
know that for sure yet.
Truth be told, nothing he's
saying makes a lot of sense.
But, they think he might
be on drugs, too,
so, they wanted to
cover their bases
and asked us to help
get a bead on the guy.
Whaddaya say?
Casino Victoria's not
too far from here.
We'll head that way now.
[TRAVIS] We got the guy's name
and address from his license.
There's a good chance
this is all bullshit.
Yeah, but we also
don't know for sure
that it's unrelated to our case.
[TRAVIS] Well, don't
say I didn't warn you.
Could be a giant waste of time.
Right. Thanks for the heads up,
but I'd like to check
it out anyway, to be safe.
[TRAVIS]
Your call.
[DOUG]
Thanks. See ya.
That's weird.
Doesn't seem like the boss wants
us to get involved with this.
Yeah.
[TRAVIS grunts]
You seem upset, Travis.
Penny for your thoughts?
Well, to be perfectly frank,
this isn't a great look
for our department.
Why? The brass okayed
the thing, right?
[TRAVIS]
Yes, indeed they did.
But, still, if something
were to happen,
the blame would land
in my lap, you know?
Oh. I just can't wait
until I have enough clout
to force things like
this on other people.
You know, most
people hide the fact
that they're pieces of shit.
[exhales]
[NARRATOR]
That's right!
Travis had a damn good reason
to be feeling on edge!
Because there was
something unexpected
waiting for Doug and Kirill
down in Marinaurben!
Something that every
officer on the force,
from detectives
down to traffic cops,
has thought about at least once!
[TRAVIS]
Police Twenty-four, what a joke.
[SHOW HOST] Welcome back to
Lisvaletta Police Twenty-Four.
[SHOW HOST] Luminox Port,
the largest and busiest port
in all of Marinaurben.
With extravagant homes
lining every street,
and luxury hotels and
casinos at its center,
it's one of the most expensive
areas in Lisvaletta.
The job of protecting its
citizens falls squarely
on the shoulders of Lisvaletta
Police Department Number Eight,
known on the streets here
as L.V.P.D. number eight.
Just after six PM,
a typical call came in about
a drunk causing trouble
at an area casino.
Constables Brown and Smith,
who were the officers
on night duty,
rushed to the scene
to investigate.
[CONSTABLE SMITH]
Let's go.
[SHOW HOST] On any given
evening, many drunks
like this one can be found
on Lisvaletta streets.
However, on this occasion,
the man in question demanded
that the mayor be called
to the scene immediately.
No one could make heads
or tails of his rant,
and police were getting nowhere.
Constable Brown
suspected the man may
have been under the influence
of an unusual street drug,
and called for backup from HQ.
A specially trained duo
of narcotics detectives
arrived on the scene.
[KIRILL]
(bleep) reporting.
[SHOW HOST] The pair who
responded to the call
were a veteran detective
and his rookie partner,
who is in his first
year on the force.
These men are part of a division
specializing in
certain drug cases.
[DOUG]
What's the deal, mister?
You been drinking a lot tonight?
[DRUNKARD 6A] Hey, sometimes
you just need a little sauce,
damn it! This guy knows
what I mean, right, officer?
[DOUG]
Of course I do.
Why don't we take this
to the squad car, buddy?
[DOUG]
So, where you from, mister?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
From above!
Upstairs, you know what I mean?
[DOUG]
Above? Above where?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
A while ago, you see.
[DOUG]
Ah, I gotcha.
Uh. But the other officers
are saying that they
don't know where "above" is. Uh.
What should I tell 'em?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
What?
You mean I gotta go over
the whole damn thing again?
Listen up, officers.
There's a whole other
world around here.
Up above!
It's the world above us,
and that is where I am from.
[DOUG]
Oh. The world above, huh?
You mean that building?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
No! Farther up!
Way, way, way farther up!
The second floor.
[KIRILL]
The second floor?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Huh?
[KIRILL]
What's the matter?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Hey, man.
You've got a face like a woman!
Don't freak me out like that!
[KIRILL growls]
[DRUNKARD 6A]
You could've killed me!
Almost scared me
to death! [laughs]
[DOUG laughing]
Now, don't go dying.
We wouldn't want
to have to arrest
one of our own for murder.
[DRUNKARD 6A] But, officer.
I guess I'm getting' old,
'cause I've been feelin'
like crap lately.
My eyesight's been all blurry.
[KIRILL] That's 'cause
you're drunk, though.
[DRUNKARD 6A] No, it's
the same during the day!
You'll never believe this,
but sometimes I see two suns!
[KIRILL]
There's always two suns. Duh.
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Oh, yeah, that's right. [laughs]
[KIRILL]
Yeah, he might be a user.
[DOUG]
Eh. No bruises, though.
So, you're some kind
of leader, mister?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Leader?
[DOUG] The leader of
an organization, right?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Oh, right, right.
It's called, um. Es... Es...
Es...
I'm pretty much the
leader of Esmeralda!
You ever heard of Esmeralda,
girly-face Tenderfoot?
[KIRILL] Well, sure.
Of course I've heard of it.
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Ha, ha! Yeah? Well, I haven't.
[KIRILL]
Huh?!
[SHOW HOST] The man most
likely had far too much
to drink, as his thoughts
seemed to drift in and out,
between reality and fantasy.
However, the officers know
exactly how to handle him.
Though they seem to
simply be listening,
the truth is much more nuanced.
[DRUNKARD 6A]
So, where's the mayor, then?
Shouldn't he be here by now?
[KIRILL] Why do you need
to talk the mayor, sir?
[DRUNKARD 6A] This world is
just a big experiment being run
by the people who live above it.
Hey, officer.
You get it, don'tcha?
[DOUG]
Sure do.
[DRUNKARD 6A] And I'm the one
who found out the truth!
They're using us
all as guinea pigs!
And if anything's gonna change,
we've gotta let somebody pretty
important know about it!
[DOUG] Yeah, sure.
I think you're right.
[DRUNKARD 6A] Right, but that's
not as easy as you'd think,
you know. 'Cause I ain't
no blabbermouth.
[KIRILL]
Well, which is it?
[DOUG]
Okay, sit still,
we're just gonna run
a quick test on you.
[DRUNKARD 6A]
A test? What kind of test?
[DOUG] We just have to find
out if you're sick or not.
[DRUNKARD 6A] Hey!
You're a doctor and an officer?
'Cause that's crazy!
[DOUG] Nah, I ain't a doctor,
and I'm not an officer, either.
[DRUNKARD 6A] I'm not sick,
okay! Please, no tests!
[DOUG]
I know you're not sick.
'Cause if you were, you'd've
called a doctor, not us.
[DRUNKARD 6A] Ha, ha. Yeah,
you're right about that.
[SHOW HOST]
The veteran knows the ropes.
He easily keeps the confused
drunk off his guard,
while he and the rookie
start running tests
for various narcotics.
Eventually, the drunk begins
to trust the pair, and he slowly
starts to calm down.
[DRUNKARD 6A]
Hey, when do I get to go home?
[DOUG] Eh. We're almost done,
so hold tight, okay?
[DRUNKARD 6A groans]
Hey, detective.
Am I arrested?
Do I get to go home?
[DOUG] Sure, if we don't find
anything, you're free.
[DRUNKARD 6A] I got a ton of
missed calls from my wife,
and that's bad!
[KIRILL]
Of course you do,
you've been out
drinking, mister.
[DRUNKARD 6A cries]
She's gonna be so pissed!
[DOUG]
Is your wife that scary?
[DRUNKARD 6A]
I'm sorry, detective!
Can't we just let this go and
pretend it never happened?
[DOUG] That sounds like a
question for your wife, not me.
[DRUNKARD 6A] Look, can you
be a real buddy and put in
a good word for me
with her? Please?
[SHOW HOST]
In the end,
all the drug tests
came back negative,
and the detectives were relieved
to find that the drunk
wasn't some big crime boss.
The suspect was given
a stern warning,
before being released
to the care of his wife,
with whom he
returned home safely.
She apologized profusely
for the disturbance.
Goodbye, sir!
Make sure you pace yourself if
you drink again in the future!
That's the dumbest
crap I've ever seen.
Well, it's not likely to lead to
any problems for us, at least.
Yeah. Sophie said
the same. I'm glad.
We dodged a bullet.
Lucky. Man, I wish I
could've been on TV.
Huh?!
[clattering]
[KIRILL laughing]
[MAXINE]
Hey. What's the big joke?
Huh? What? Me?
[YURI]
Hm?
All right. I'll be going, then.
See ya.
[KIRILL]
Hey, old lady!
Did you record the
show like I asked?
Yes, will you shut up?
Here you go.
How stupid. Are you seriously
gonna save that thing?
You bet your old-lady ass!
Getting the chance
to be on this show
has always been a dream of mine!
Huh? Wait a minute, I thought
your dream was to be a hero!
[KIRILL]
Yeah that, too.
I got lotsa dreams,
and this was one!
[KIRILL gasping]
[inhales] It would've been
perfect if I'd talked more!
[SHOW HOST]
The veteran knows the ropes.
He easily keeps the confused
drunk off his guard...
Doug really is the coolest!
Man, I wish I would've
said something dope!
"And then!
Something strange
caught the officer's eye!
Over there!" Like that!
Uh?
[gasps]
[KIRILL gasps]
[KIRILL] That's crazy. Something
really did catch my eye.
The person I've been searching
for all these years.
[KIRILL]
Doug! Hey, Doug!
Where are you?!
I'm pretty sure he's still
in the AV analysis room.
[KIRILL]
There you are!
We have to go back to that
crime scene, right now!
[DOUG]
You saw it, too, didn't you?
[gasps] Yeah, how could I not?
[KIRILL] Even after ten years,
I could tell.
That was none other
than my sister, Milla.
My missing sister!
I already know where
to look. C'mon.
[gasos]
[KIRILL]
So, you saw what I saw?
Of course I did.
I've done my homework.
I see.
Quite a stroke of luck.
Yeah.
[DOUG] Sometimes those dumb
TV shows can come in handy.
I'm amazed, though.
I don't know how you
could tell from that.
[DOUG]
Hm? Is that an insult?
Not at all.
[KIRILL]
I feel dumb.
Of course, he would see it,
he's much more perceptive
than I could ever be.
[NARRATOR] Correct!
And you are, too, viewers,
so I'm sure you've
already figured out
what's goin' on here.
What Doug actually
saw in the video
was something else entirely.
He spotted the wanted
pack mule they were after!
It wasn't Kirill's sister,
Milla, at all!
[KIRILL]
Oh, Milla.
I'm sad you live in
a place like this.
[KIRILL] What are we waiting
for? Let's get going!
[DOUG]
Don't rush it.
We don't get a chance
like this often.
So, we gotta be careful
not to spook our target.
[KIRILL] Come on, it's not
like we're after a criminal!
Yeah. I guess we don't
want to be abrupt.
Oh, man. Who knew
I'd be so nervous?
Hey, Doug.
What do you think I should say,
when we're finally face-to-face?
[DOUG]
Hm?
It's best to act natural,
like it's no big deal, right?
I'm sure it's gonna
be quite a shock.
Uh... Well. I mean,
it is shocking.
I guess.
I have no idea what to say.
No need to say anything
out of the ordinary.
Best to keep it simple!
I think so, too!
[DOUG]
Hm?
[KIRILL]
It's so surreal,
how life puts people right
in your path sometimes.
[DOUG]
That's how it seems to work.
[KIRILL] But, how did you know
to come here, of all places?
[DOUG]
The security cameras.
Marinaurben is a
very affluent area.
Lots of money means
more protection.
So, every part of town is
covered by these cameras.
There's hardly a square inch
out of sight around here.
[gasps]
They're pretty helpful.
If you know what your
target looks like, well,
then they're much
easier to trace.
I guess that makes sense.
[DOUG] But, since there's so
much footage to wade through,
you gotta put a lot
of man hours into it.
That's the hard part.
[yawns]
[KIRILL]
Oh, Doug.
I can't believe you went
through all that for me!
What do you mean--
it wasn't for you.
[KIRILL]
Thank you so much, Doug.
After all these years,
I get to see Mi--
[thud]
What time do you have,
Constable Vrubel?
--[KIRILL] Huh?
--Time.
[gasps] Right about 13:20.
As of 13:20, in accordance
with Lisvaletta city-state code,
you are hereby under arrest
for violating Anthem
Prohibition Act. Article Ten.
Bullshit! How did
you guys find me?
[KIRILL] Hey, Doug. Is this
who you saw on the video?
Yeah. It's him. No doubt.
[CRIMINAL 6A]
How'd you do it?!
How were you able to find me?!
[KIRILL growls]
Your sister?
Yeah.
I saw my missing sister in the
Police Twenty-four video, too.
So, the whole time, I thought
this was about finding her.
I remember you saying
you wanted to find her,
but how would I even know
what she looked like?
I thought that part
was kinda weird.
But I just figured
you were smart.
And you're absolutely sure
the woman you saw was her?
Uh. Yeah.
I guess we could look through
the footage, from the cameras.
[KIRILL]
Well. I mean,
she's not a criminal
or anything like that.
Would they even
give us access to it
just for a regular citizen?
There is another way.
[DOUG] He's got some kind
of weird system in place.
One that allows him to watch all
the security camera footage
at the touch of a few buttons.
Looks like your
peeping tom habit's
actually coming
in handy for once.
Doctor Apple.
I only use it to help develop
the support structure, Doug!
It's a big part of
my job, you know!
[KIRILL]
Wow, you're just incredible!
Call me Doctor.
[KIRILL]
Serious peeping tom skills.
[gasps]
[DOUG chuckles]
[APPLE grunts, clears throat]
This is her, right?
[gasps]
[APPLE] I can use this
video to track her.
It's gonna take a
little time, though.
[inhales]
[DOUG] How long did you
say it's been, again?
Since you last saw her.
Uh. Since I was about 10
years old, and Milla was 19.
So, a full decade.
And is she your only family?
Well, there was Grandfather.
We weren't related
by blood, though.
So... Your grandfather,
what's he like?
You're a whole lot
more inquisitive
than usual, what gives?
Do you still live with
your grandfather, then?
I don't. While I was
at the academy, he--
Anyway, we don't live together.
Not sure if he's why Milla left.
[DOUG]
I see.
Grandfather was the
difficult, quiet type.
I make up that he and Milla
didn't get along very well.
But I was just a kid, so I don't
know if I remember it right.
In any case, that's something
I'll ask if I see her.
[KIRILL]
It's so strange.
She just disappeared
without a word one day.
I wanna ask her why.
[KIRILL]
You weren't able to trace her?
No, she went into a public
restroom after this.
Tried everything I could,
but I still wasn't able
to pick up the trail.
[KIRILL]
I see.
Question. Did she do something
she'd feel guilty about?
Why do you ask?
[APPLE] She seems to
be intentionally avoiding
the cameras for some reason.
Oh. Well, there's
nothing I know of.
Okay. Well, don't let
it get you down.
Facial analysis works well.
So, there's a high
probability that's her.
We're very likely
to find something.
Thank you very much, Doctor.
No sweat.
I'll keep an eye out for
any new leads for you.
I'll be in touch.
Nice work, Doctor.
Uh?
[KIRILL]
It's great.
Before, I had no idea
if she was even alive.
Just knowing that
she's doing all right--
it's a big step forward.
I'm so happy for you.
You became a policeman
to find her, and look,
it already happened.
I guess even dummies
can get things done
with hard work. Nice.
[laughs] I didn't even do
any of the work.
Hey there, sorry to interrupt
the sentimental soiree,
but may I have your attention
for just a brief moment?
I wanted to introduce you
guys to my part-timer,
she started today!
It's weird. She says she
can't tell me too much
about her identity
and background,
but I'm ignoring
that red flag 'cause,
like the name of
the bar implies,
it's my place and
I do whatever I want.
[KIRILL]
Milla!
[KIRILL sputtering]
Kirill! Is that you?
So, this is the sister
you've been searching for
all this time, well,
imagine that! Heh!
I mean.
If I had known, I probably
would've told you sooner.
So, why'd you abandon
your little brother?
[DERICK]
Yeah. Tell us why!
Deana, stop!
It's fine. I had no
good reason, honestly.
Just young and stupid, I guess.
[DEANA] Well, where have you
been hiding all these years?
Oh, you know, here and there.
[KAY] What led you to seek
work here, of all places?
I wanted to work in a bar
that wouldn't be likely
to draw big crowds,
and this place fit the bill.
Because you...
don't like attention?
Yeah, I guess.
Or something like that.
Then this place is perfect!
I can't see it ever
being popular--
to be honest, he probably
shouldn't've hired staff.
[DERICK grunts]
I'm just glad you're
doing well, Kirill.
So, you're a police officer?
Say something, stupid!
What's wrong? Well?
Weren't you going
to ask her something?
You're wrong, kid.
You don't want to
know why she left.
There's another question
that's eating you up inside.
What you're really dying
to ask is why your sister
didn't take you with her.
When you dig right down to
the bedrock, that's the truth.
Maybe.
I'm sure she had a
good reason for that.
[DOUG] Sparrows and swallows
can't comprehend the aspirations
of phoenixes and swans.
Know what I mean?
That's true.
Sparrows, swallows,
phoenixes, and swans.
[DOUG] It's cool if you don't
know what that means.
Yeah. I'll look it up later.
[MILLA grunts]
[KIRILL] It's okay. We don't
have to talk about it now.
What matters is we got
to see each other.
Thanks, Kirill.
Someday, whenever
you feel ready to,
you can tell me then.
Ha, ha! Aw, baby
brother's crying!
[KIRILL]
I am not!
[KAY] There's nothing wrong
with being emotional, okay?
What the hell are you
blubbering about?!
It makes sense for this guy
to be all weepy, but you?
You all seem to be such
a close-knit group.
It's quite a relief.
I was worried, but it seems
like my little brother
has made some great friends.
I don't know.
They're not friends.
That's the wrong word.
[DOUG]
Yeah. We're comrades.
[KIRILL snores]
Wake up, buddy, time to go.
[KIRILL grunts]
Okay.
Little boys' room's that way.
Yeah, yeah, I know that!
[APPLE] Doug! Do you ever
answer your phone?!
[DOUG]
Oh, Doctor.
I forgot to invite
you out. My bad.
No, I don't care.
I mean, yes I do!
Damn, which is it?
[APPLE]
I, uh, found something out
that Kirill might want to know.
[MILLA grunts]
[yelps] Milla!
Seriously?
Yeah! A security camera at
the train station recorded it.
Kirill's sister very clearly
went into the men's
restroom there.
But, like.
Why were you watching?
Doug asked me to look into
the whole sister thing.
Uh! I-- I-I wasn't trying
to peep in the bathrooms,
if that's what
you're all thinking!
I'm creating a support system!
[DEANA] Uh, nobody was
even thinking that.
Back up to the man part.
Nobody understands what
you're trying to say.
Oh. I see. I wasn't
peeping, though.
[sputters]
[MILLA] I'm sorry I never told
you the truth about me, Kirill.
My given name
isn't Milla, actually.
[gasping]
[MILLA] That's how
you know me, but...
My real name is Valery Vrubel.
[KIRILL gasps]
I planned to
tell you eventually.
[NARRATOR]
Kirill finally reunites
with his estranged sister!
But then, that other idiot
decides to take action,
lest we forget there's another
protagonist in this show!
They're all so insecure!
Next time on Double Decker,
episode Seven:
"Revenge is Mine!"
You should be watching!