[NARRATOR]
Meet the very first gun
capable of firing
anti-AMS bullets.
The AP-zero-one, or, "Sylvia."
And that pretty boy
holding said gun
is the young genius
known as Doctor!
[DEANA] Hey, Apple!
I'm checking out a type one.
[DEANA] You hear a word
I just said, Apple Bieber?
Doctor Apple!
[MAXINE] This thing needs
maintenance yesterday, Apple.
It's "Doctor!"
Thanks for everything, Apple.
[APPLE] You bastards.
Call me, "Doctor!"
[panting]
[KAY]
You okay?
[APPLE] How long's it take
for an Eye System scan?
About 4.5 seconds.
Even the most
experienced detective
will lose a few seconds.
So, that means
you guys can't miss.
That's why we let you
customize 'em.
They can be rifles
or handguns, too.
That said. For now,
start with a Sylvia.
If you start with a model
you're not ready to handle--
[KIRILL yelps]
[KAY gasps]
[APPLE]
Well, you get the picture.
Oh, yeah. I'll take one
of these bad boys.
[KIRILL] This is the SCIU!
Whoosh! Whooshy-whoosh!
I've got you now, punk!
Pa-Pow!
So freakin' bad ass.
[KIRILL yelps]
How long've you been there?
Since, "Whoosh!
Whooshy-whoosh" or around then.
[KIRILL]
Kill me now!
Anyway, we've got a meeting,
Constable Vrubel.
[KIRILL groans]
Hey, hold on.
[DOUG]
Hm?
We don't have to be
so formal, you know.
Just call me "Kirill,"
or "Partner,'
if that's what you'd
prefer. Cool?
Oh. Sure. Whatever.
C'mon, Constable.
[KIRILL]
Did you hear what I just said?!
[TRAVIS] They pick up the
stuff in the Ignuscastrum
industrial zone from
someone they call
"Bamboo Man,"
which is pretty lame.
He's always wearing a mask,
so they've never seen his face.
But he's got jewels for teeth,
as you can see here.
Kinda defeats the
purpose of the mask.
The buyer has no idea
where this Bamboo cat
is getting all the Anthem.
And that's where we come in.
[DOUG] We go undercover,
find the place,
then burn it to the ground.
Yeah, you and me, Dougie!
That's right, Buzz-cut.
You're quick, huh?
All right, partner,
let's kick ass!
Do you even know what
"undercover" means?
Lucky you, Doug.
Trying to search an
entire industrial zone?
That's like throwing darts at
a fly with a blindfold on.
I don't judge you
for your kinks, Doug,
I know we can do it!
Yeah, Buzz-cut,
give 'im what for!
Look, my mind says no.
Should we accompany them
on the investigation, then?
I mean, it was our case
to begin with, remember?
[TRAVIS]
Actually, I think it would be
a good training
exercise for the kid.
[KAY gasps]
I think this might be
a local paper from
southwest Ignis!
[KIRILL] Huh? How could you
have any way of knowing that?
[KAY] Well, look,
they're eating Ignis pie,
which is a local delicacy.
Yeah, so, what?
It's a color photo, too.
Seems fancy for a piece
on a small strike.
To me, it says that
it's a local outfit.
Nice work. I hate combing
through microfiches.
Efficiency's the name
of the game.
Excellent catch, there, Rookie.
Oh, no. It's not a big deal.
[DEANA] 'Kay. You just earned
a trip to southwest Ignis.
[KAY, KIRILL gasp]
[DEANA] Travis called it
a training exercise,
so get trained.
You're just sick of
babysitting her.
Is that okay?
Yes, I think Pink's
onto something here.
[KIRILL grumbles]
[DOUG]
Hm? Hey, what's wrong?
[KIRILL] This is our first
case together as partners,
and now it's totally
ruined, and it sucks!
I hoped we could bond,
but now she'll be there!
We don't get to
choose our partners.
[KIRILL]
Uh. Huh?
You don't get to pick
your parents, do you?
Or where you're born?
[KIRILL grunts]
If you're gonna skip town,
the least you could do
is pay rent first.
[gasps] Haven't I told you
to stay out of my room?
And I'm just going on
a business trip!
Oh, can I ask a favor?
Water my plants while
I'm gone, will ya?
Yeah, yeah, fine.
[KIRILL] Okay, toothbrush,
extra socks, what else?
Relationship problems got you
down in the dumps, kid?
Whoa, no way! You could tell?
[NARRATOR]
"Struggling with relationships.
How to deepen connections
in ways even a monkey--"
Shut up, crone! It's
not even like that.
[LANDLADY]
This might help.
Don't you know the old saying?
The fastest way to a person's
heart is through their stomach?
Thank you! Old lady!
Donuts! I passed by and thought,
since we're cops and all.
Nah. I'm trying to
eat fewer carbs.
[gasps]
Eat 'em.
[DOUG] The Southwestern region's
known as an industrial hot spot.
Most of the country's crude oil
gets refined down here.
The factory districts
are like labyrinths.
Hence, the gondolas.
They're the primary
means of transportation.
Apparently, the local police
have set up security checkpoints
at the gondola loading zones
from time to time,
but they haven't been very
effective thus far.
[KIRILL] I already know how
all this is gonna go down.
I'm gonna kick ass!
Do something amazing and heroic!
[DOUG]
You saved me, buddy!
[KIRILL]
Naturally, buddy.
I'm your buddy, after all.
[NARRATOR] Even his fantasies
lack imagination!
Loser!
Oh, I get it. So, you're saying
that the only factory
capable of producing such
large amounts of
Anthem is GG Oil's?
That's right. Smart.
[KIRILL]
I've gotta deepen our bond
before the moment
of truth arrives!
I'm starving. Bummer.
[gasps] Hey, Kay, stop
hogging all the do--
Right. It's time to
bake this cookie!
Kirill, wait. Your weapon...
So, what now, partner?
Are we bustin' in, or--?
Lose the gun.
Carry this instead.
Wha--?!
[DOUG] We can't do crap
without any evidence.
So, to get it, we'll pretend
we're a TV news crew!
[KIRILL]
What the--?
It's too crowded for
us to just sneak in.
And what kind of story are we
supposed to be covering here?
Take a guess.
[JOEL] Workers are entitled
to our rights!
[WORKERS]
Workers' Rights!
[JOEL]
We built this place!
We won't be treated
like factory waste!
[WORKERS] We won't be
treated like factory--!
We don't get days off,
and we barely even
get paid for our work.
I can't afford to buy
milk for my daughter,
let alone new socks!
Whoa, seriously?
Yeah, why?
[KIRILL]
Uh. Nothing, uh--
So, tell me, how long have
you all been on strike?
[sighs] It's coming
up on six months.
You've been out of
work for that long?
[door creaks]
[HARRY ] "Feed the blazing fire,
until the flames of hope
burn every last fool to
cinders and ash." Poetry.
I'm the union head,
Harry Botoms.
[KIRILL]
Hairy bottoms...?
[HARRY coughs]
I'm sorry.
I have an advanced lung disease.
Oh, that's awful.
And he got it from exposure
to the factory's gas fumes!
The owners lie, claiming to have
no knowledge of its effect.
His health's faded.
He destroyed it trying
to help others.
To make sure no one else
had to endure his plight.
Really? Why go so far?
They built this empire
on the workers' backs,
exploiting and abusing us
the whole time.
I refuse to roll over and
let them get away with it.
[KIRILL gasping]
[KIRILL] This guy's what
I call a true hero!
[JOEL] We're fine here.
You should go get some rest.
[DOUG]
Oh, sorry.
[HARRY] These things happen.
You need some help?
I'm fine, thanks.
[KIRILL]
Good job, Kay!
I hope management
agrees to our terms soon
and we can reach a compromise.
[KIRILL]
Well, um.
[JOEL, HARRY]
Huh?
Hang in there, okay?
Didn't see our guy.
The Bamboo Man.
No union members
had jeweled teeth.
Although, I can't imagine he
would be a union worker.
Those men can't
even buy socks!
How could they afford
jeweled teeth?
I suspect the factory fat cats!
Fine. To the factory, then.
[KAY, KIRILL]
Huh?
Whelp. This here
is the factory floor.
[DOUG] Is that so
you can pouch the oil?
[KIRILL] I guess this is
what he was talking about.
[TOMMY] No, that's left over
from a long time ago.
[DOUG]
Left over?
We used to manufacture
asphalt, plastics,
all kinds of other
petroleum products,
but, now, as you can see...
[FACTORY WORKERS cough]
[TOMMY] All we do is load
the refined heavy oil
onto the trucks and send
it off to distributors--
[gasps]
[KIRILL] Are you willing to
negotiate with the union?
What are you doing?
Look, kid, if we listened
to every little thing
the union bitched about,
we'd be out of business
before the end of the week.
But Harry and those guys
contracted lung
disease working here!
[TOMMY] You got any proof
to back up that claim?
What else could it be?!
[TOMMY] When you jump
to conclusions like that,
you cost good men their jobs.
It makes things worse for
all of us in the long run.
Says who?
[TOMMY]
Tch. Huh?!
Hey, stop that!
This conveyor belt's
cleaner than the others.
[TOMMY]
Well, we're in the middle
of doing maintenance
on it right now.
Don't you have better things
to do with company funds?
You're taking all this
pretty seriously.
[KIRILL]
Of course, why wouldn't I?
[gasps]
[DOUG] It's not enough
to justify a raid.
But, that was the exact
same newspaper
that the Anthem was wrapped in.
[DOUG]
Don't be a snob.
Factory foremen
read the paper, too.
Then I guess we'll just have
to gather more evidence
the old-fashioned way.
[yawns] We'll find what we're
looking for somehow.
[STRIKER 3A] Look where
you're aiming, dammit!
[STRIKER 3B grunting]
[splash]
[KIRILL groans]
Ah! Whoa, are you all right?
[KIRILL]
Hey! Take this, ya stupid j--
[screaming]
[WORKERS laugh]
[DOUG]
Damn. Zero core strength.
Yeah, he fell flat on his butt
at the firing range, too.
[DOUG]
What's wrong?
Nothing. But I'm staying here.
Huh?
A detective's instinct!
There's something
fishy going on.
[DOUG]
Ah. Word. See ya.
[DOUG] You'll need it
for your stake out.
Catch you later. We're
heading back to the hotel.
[KIRILL]
Oh. Sure.
But... Is this safe?
That camera's a lot
heavier than it looks.
[phone ringing]
[KIRILL]
You just wait and see. Buddy.
[WORKER muttering]
[DOUG]
Kay and I talked it over.
We decided to search around
on the east side tomorrow.
[KIRILL]
Roger.
I'm gonna hang out here
a little longer.
[DOUG] How's that "Detective's
Instinct" workin' out for ya?
[KIRILL]
You know how this stuff goes!
[gasps]
It's doing just fine!
Wait, are you certain?
[DOUG] He said he saw six
trucks leaving the factory.
That much oil?
With only one working
belt? Not likely.
[DOUG]
Is what he said.
[KIRILL]
Don't think. Feel so good!
[TRAVIS] Why don't we ping
the local police for back-up?
[DOUG] I get why you'd suggest
that, but I think it's too late.
Will he be all right?
You suckers aren't
getting through tonight!
[FACTORY DRIVER 3A]
Hey, are you okay in there?
[FACTORY DRIVER 3B]
What's the matter?
Bam, bitches.
All six trucks. Just oil.
No Anthem anywhere.
[KIRILL] Yeah, but they were
driving without headlights.
[DOUG] They said they
do that as a precaution,
because they get pummeled with
eggs and bricks if they don't.
Hate to say it.
Instinct failed you.
[KIRILL]
Oh, shut up!
[KIRILL sighs]
[KIRILL] He's wishing he was
here with Derick and not me.
He thinks I'm a crappy partner.
[door clicks]
[APPLE]
Derick?
Yeah, of course I know him, duh.
Mr. Billingham's
last partner, right?
Wait, Mr. Billingham?
We're not on first name terms.
It'd feel weird--
[KIRILL] I didn't call
to talk about Doug.
Derick was the best
partner a cop could have.
[KIRILL gasps]
He had fantastic intuition,
and knew exactly how to
support Mr. Billingham.
I miss him quite a bit.
It's sad to think I'll never
see them in action again.
Also, you'd better bring back
the gun you swiped from my lab--
Hello.
[gasps]
Wanna go grab something
to eat with me?
[KAY] I've been hoping
to get a chance
to talk to you alone
for a while, Kirill.
But this trip's
been super-crazy.
We've been busy
ever since we got here.
Tonight'll be my big
chance, though!
[KIRILL]
What's she doing?
Is this her way of trying
to make me feel better,
or something? Why
would she do that?
I wanted to thank you
for the donuts, too.
[KIRILL]
Oh, crap!
Did I worm my way into
her heart instead?!
[KAY]
Oh! This is the place!
[KIRILL] She even picked out
a special restaurant for us!
Ignis pie! I've always
wanted to try it...
[KIRILL] And look at all
those bookmarks!
She really went all out!
That's just adorable!
[NARRATOR] Kirill was making
more of this than it was.
She's not into him at all!
She's just a raging foodie!
I mean, we're here, right?
We have to enjoy
the local delicacies,
or we'll be missing out!
How sweet.
She really cares.
It's too awkward to come and
eat in a place like this alone.
I feel so valued, what a gal!
[NARRATOR] These kids
don't know how to listen!
[HARRY] He who refuses to listen
is no better than swine.
Blind to his foolishness, until
the butcher chops off his head.
[JOEL] That's insulting
to pigs, don't ya think?
Thigs are delicious, but they're
smarter than most other animals.
[HARRY grunts]
[phone ringing]
[HARRY] It all worked out
exactly as I said it would.
[TOMMY] Do you think that means
the heat's off of us?
[HARRY]
Yeah, but stay sharp anyway.
[TOMMY] So, you don't think
they're angry with us, do you?
[HARRY]
Everything's fine.
I'm on my way to
the deal site now.
[TOMMY] I'd really like to meet
this Bamboo Man someday.
Is that so--
You are not worthy of that.
You're nothing more than swine.
Let's get outta here.
[DOUG]
So, the gondolas themselves
were the transport method.
That's a pretty clever ruse.
It got you through
the checkpoints.
You're with that
TV station, right?
What are you doin'
out here this late?
[DOUG] I didn't trust you,
right from the beginning.
So, I kept an eye on you.
Whoa, what are you
talkin' about?
[DOUG]
You saw that ridiculous picture.
When the papers
fell to the floor.
I clocked your panic
when you did.
And if you did have any sort of
connection to the Bamboo Man
matter, I knew seeing that photo
would spur you into action.
[HARRY] Of course I looked
at that stupid photo.
Who wouldn't have a reaction
to seeing a man with
rubies for teeth?
You saw that much?
I'm surprised you
could even tell
it was a shot of a man's face.
[HARRY gasps]
You realized in that
moment that someone
was onto your little
operation here.
So, you called
the factory foreman.
Gave him a heads up to hide
the goods and let us in.
And then you sent out
the trucks as decoys
to distract us from
the real drop.
You'd shake us clean
off your tails.
So, you could go right back
to selling the Anthem.
[HARRY] These accusations
are absolutely ridiculous.
What proof do you have
to back them up?
Instinct and hunches aren't
probable cause, by the way.
Tell me about that
book of poems.
What, factory men aren't
allowed to read poetry?
[DOUG]
That one you had.
It's a limited edition.
I saw the serial number.
[DOUG] You could buy a
year's worth of new socks
with that kind of scratch.
[growls]
[DOUG] Why don't we continue
this at the station?
[SMUGGLERS grunting]
[SMUGGLERS groan]
[engine starts]
[SMUGGLER 3A groaning]
[exhales]
You promised I didn't
have to worry!
[HARRY]
Shut your mouth!
Just clear out everything that
hasn't been pouched yet.
[TOMMY] Why not just burn
the place down?
Destroy the evidence, and we
can collect insurance, too!
Burn the Anthem? Why?
Hell no!
[TOMMY] "Anthem"? What
in the world is Anthem?
[HARRY] Listen. If you
set fire to the place,
Esperanza will kill you!
What?! You never said
that I was in danger.
I'm starting to think you
haven't been very--
Dammit!
What is this stuff, anyway?
[BAMBOO MAN] You have no
idea the danger you're in.
[TOMMY whimpers]
[BAMBOO MAN]
If you die now,
will you go to heaven--
or burn in hell?
[TOMMY groaning]
[BAMBOO MAN laughs]
Tomorrow, let's both
do our best, okay?
What? Oh, yeah.
I'm really grateful you and I
are getting to work together!
Wow, this girl is super
aggressive, isn't she?
[KAY gasps]
[KIRILL gasping]
[HARRY grunting]
It's Harry!
[KIRILL]
Are you all right, sir?
[gun cocks]
Drop your gun, now!
[HARRY] C'mon, move,
you government pigs.
Aww, dammit. Is the
Bamboo Man already here?
This is where they
made all the Anthem?
Now. Gather up everything
lying around on the floor.
Harry, why? It's wrong.
The factory's greed is
what drove me to do this.
So I'm just fighting back.
There's nothing wrong with that!
But, you--
You claimed to be fighting
the good fight!
I need to make money!
I refuse to die in poverty,
no matter what it takes!
That doesn't mean--
Shut up! This isn't my fault!
It isn't my fault!
[DOUG]
Hold it right there.
[KIRILL]
Doug!
Let him go and
come out, or die!
[HARRY] Just try it, and I'll
blow the kid's brains out!
[TOMMY]
Brilliant!
[BOTH gasp]
[KIRILL]
Who's that?
[DOUG grunts]
[TOMMY laughs]
Harry! Anthem feels so good!
I had no idea!
This stuff's just like heaven!
Anthem induced Overdrive!
That's great, Tommy!
Now be a pal and crush
these detectives, will ya?
You shut your mouth!
I don't take orders anymore!
Tommy, no.
You always leave me out
of important stuff.
You make fun of me all the time!
[HARRY] We can talk about
that later, just kill them!
I said... I don't take orders!
[HARRY groans]
I am invincible!
No one will make fun
of me ever again!
No one can tell me what to do!
[KAY]
Are you okay?
Yeah. What the hell
happened here?
The foreman. He went
into Anthem Overdrive.
He's lost control.
[DOUG]
Activating Eye System.
[TOMMY]
I am invincible!
He's big, but he's fast,
too. I can't get a scan.
Well, first... We've got to
slow him down somehow,
without getting
in too close.
Invincible, are ya?
[gasps]
[TOMMY]
Huh...?
Even now, you're still the
same loser no one listens to.
You idiot!
What did you say to me?
[TOMMY grunts]
[gasps]
[KIRILL]
All it'll take is one shot!
I've got a gun in the car.
It's special.
Made specifically for morons
like you, you giant loaf!
[KIRILL groans]
[KAY]
Kirill, no!
Doug! Hurry up and fire, now!
I don't do things this way.
It's reckless.
I get it, fine! Just hurry!
[exhales] Right.
Time for your medicine.
[gunshot]
[KIRILL] So, then, GG oil was
just a dummy company.
They were subcontracted
to put the Anthem
into patches for distribution?
[DOUG]
Yeah. Oh, you'll like this.
I heard the union guys are gonna
be rebuilding the factory.
[KIRILL] That's great. They'll
be able to afford socks now.
Socks? Oh, right.
[KIRILL]
Mm?
[DOUG]
Here, got you a lighter model.
Flashy and powerful.
It's perfect for you, right?
[gasping] You got me this?
Hey, Doug!
[DOUG]
Hm?
Could we talk about
your partner?
You know, the one
who passed away.
When you're ready to.
A-And only if you're up
for it, of course.
[APPLE]
Was that ridiculous gun for him?
Makes sense. It suits
his personality, I guess.
Huh? What are you
talking about?
Bang! Bang!
Bang!
[DOUG]
He's talking about my partner.
[NARRATOR] Kirill renews his
resolve to be
the best partner ever to Doug!
But a terrible misunderstanding
threatens to blow the whole
thing up in his face!
That's right.
It was all in his head!
Next time, on Double Decker !
Episode four: "Derick returns!"
Time for a dose
of reality, chump!