[COOPER]
As of right now,
we haven't managed to
track down Zabel yet.
But, the latest case
made one thing quite clear.
If we're ever going to take
down Esperanza for good,
we have no choice but
to combine our forces.
SEVEN-O and the military?
Yes, I must admit, I was
incredibly impressed
during the fake kidnapping.
Particularly with
the young detective
who rescued his partner.
[DOUG] It's the perfect day
for hang-drying laundry.
You're obsessed
with mundane crap!
Huh?
You damn well better have
written your report by now!
My writing hand still--
I don't care--we're not
allowed back on the streets
until you turn it in!
Hey, pretty girl, how much?
What'll this buy?
[GUS]
If I'd known you were a cop,
I never would've approached you.
You think that makes it okay?
Well, I didn't realize you
were a pretty dude, either!
Epic fail all around.
You wanna talk about this
down at the station?!
[growls]
[DOUG] Stop. Just let
him have a warning.
But this punk clearly
intended to--
You don't just look like a girl,
you act like one, too.
--Yeah?! So, what?!
--[DOUG laughing]
There you are...
Sorry. I hope he wasn't
causing you any trouble.
--[KIRILL] Oh, no.
--[GUS] Come on, Pops.
You need to get back in bed.
[JEFFREY] Well, I got worried
and had to find you.
Am I free to go?
Uh. Yeah.
[GUS]
You're so sweaty.
'Scuse me, Nurse?!
Can you bring us
a wheelchair, please?
Son, I can walk back on my own.
Don't force yourself.
You're too weak!
Well, I guess he's not that bad
of a kid after all, right?
Huh?! Asshole!
[NARRATOR]
Of course, Doug is fully aware
that his partner's not allowed
back on the streets until he
fills out all his paperwork
from their previous case.
[NARRATOR]
But, Doug?
He wants some time off,
and he's damn well gettin' it!
He's in for an earful
as soon as I find him!
[DEANA]
You little piece of shit!
First of all, I ain't a hooker,
second, that's illegal,
and third, you think this
chump change'd be enough?
Look, ma'am, I wasn't
even asking you.
I was interested in a night
with your little sister.
I'll let that slide,
since you're a kid.
You're way too young
to appreciate the beauty...
Deana, calm down!
Control yourself!
Guess this twerp hasn't
learned his lesson yet.
[KAY]
Oh! Kirill!
What the--?
I guess losers of a feather
really do flock together.
[DEANA growls]
[KAY]
Deana! Stop!
[GUS grunts, laughs]
I don't know what it is, but
that kid really pisses me off.
Yeah. Me, too.
Hate to tell ya,
especially since you
made the trip down here,
but I've been chasing Doug
around the hospital
all damn day.
Well, we didn't
come to see Doug.
--[KIRILL] Huh?
--We're here on a case.
[KAY]
We've brought photographs.
They're of four people who've
died under strange circumstances
in the past few months.
Our investigation revealed that
all four of the deceased men
had a couple of things
in common. First of all,
every single one of them
was a confirmed Anthem user.
And the other commonality...
...is that they were
all former patients
of this hospital, right?
Wow.
Here you are,
running this entire joint,
yet you've still got
enough time to learn
the names and faces of
all the patients?
You're speaking to the leading
authority in end-of-life care.
This doctor... He does
everything he can--
Each of these men was informed
they didn't have long to live.
We were developing a care
plan for all of them.
But, before anything
was finalized,
they forced their way
out of the hospital.
I can understand why they'd
turn to Anthem as an escape.
They were desperate for relief.
If I didn't know better,
I'd call that an endorsement.
We endorse drugs all the time.
[DEANA]
Huh...?
Medicine or poison?
It's a fine line.
It comes down to
how the drug is used.
I wonder... Do you even
understand how Anthem
affects the human body
and its various processes?
[BOTH gasp]
[KIRILL] There's this
gene editing technology
with a really weird name I
can't remember at the moment.
Anthem works in a similar way.
It rewrites genetic code, right?
--[DEANA] Huh?!
--[DOCTORS gasp]
[DEANA]
U-Uh... Uh...
[KIRILL]
During normal gene editing,
there's always a small chance
that an error can occur.
A mutation, which can
awaken dormant genes.
What we refer to as "Overdrive,"
is really just that.
It occurs as a result of
these errors in the code.
I would imagine that Anthem
is kind of similar
to a bacteria molecule
in that way,
'cause I think bacteria contain
something called a vector.
Yeah, that does sound right.
Vectors copy genetic material
and deliver it to other cells.
Right!
They really just behave
as carriers in that way.
It's rare, but this process
can cause the genes to mutate.
And the mutations can affect
the physical body, as well.
Am I in the ballpark?
Yeah, you're basically right.
[sputtering]
[DOCTOR HOPE]
Wonderful work!
I've always dreamed of
meeting an investigator
who really knows his stuff!
[KAY]
Huh?!
If it's not too much to ask,
could you do me a little favor?
Can SEVEN-O's leadership put me
in contact with the military?
[gasps]
Dr. Hope means it.
He's appealed to the
military many times
to start clinical trials
for medical Anthem.
I'm... not sure
how to respond. Uh--
Hey. Who the hell are you?
[JEFFREY]
Pardon me.
Excuse me, sir?
Would you be so kind
as to help me?
This means a lot to me.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
[GUS]
Ladies! Can I ask you somethin'?
Do both of you have boyfriends?
[FEMALE 10A] That's none
of your business, kid.
[JEFFREY]
Poor guy...
Goin' after every girl
he sees lately.
Guess he's just at that age.
Does it worry you?
No, not at all.
Makes me happy.
That boy spends all
of his time with me.
It's gonna be hard.
He has a lot of suffering in
store for him when I go.
So, I like to see him let
loose, like a normal kid.
[laughing]
[PATIENT 10A coughing]
[PATIENT 10A]
Please... help me...
I'm not ready to die yet.
[APPLE]
That idiot? You're kidding me.
[DEANA]
No, I'm serious!
He started talking like a
totally different person.
Kay was there!
[KAY] It really seemed like
he turned into someone else!
[APPLE] Did he get into some
kind of weird drug or something?
[KIRILL]
Hey! I'm right here, you know!
Look, it doesn't
make any sense!
You're dumb, so how were you
spouting that mumbo-jumbo
about Anthem and
genes and stuff!
Well, if you must know...
[DOUG]
See, the thing about Anthem is
that it alters the human genome.
Sometimes it induces
rapid evolution,
which we call Overdrive.
The drug eliminates all your
natural, genetic limiters.
I mean, he gave me all
the basic information,
I just filled in the
blanks, you know?
Okay, I'm officially pissed off.
Told you.
[KIRILL] Why don't you guys
stop stuffing your faces
and do some work?
Are you putting something
together for this new case?
They just asked for
my help is all.
Figured I'd slap
something together.
I'm handing it in
to Travis in a bit.
Well, then, I'm happy
to lend a hand with that.
Since you only have a
rudimentary grasp of such
subjects, you should have an
expert eye checking your work.
I'll be fine, thanks.
You're an amateur--
you can't possibly do it.
[APPLE] Huh? Although, you're
wise to choose that paper.
[KIRILL]
Huh...?
That paper, there.
"On the Potentialities
of Silent Genes."
It was published when
I was just a kid.
I read it when I was 12 or
13--fascinating stuff.
I'm glad you like my work.
[ALL gasp]
You mean you wrote it?!
Inconceivable!
I had to do something to
pay my way through school!
Although, it's been
so many years
since it was published,
I've forgotten it all.
[KAY] Who abandons a career
in genetics to become a cop?
[KIRILL]
It's not like that.
I read about it in a manga
and thought it was kinda cool.
So, I studied up.
[STUDENT 10A]
Kirill, you're crazy, man!
"Kinda cool"...?
Kirill has been a genius
this entire time?
Stop, I am by no means
a genius, come on.
I just busted my hump
on that one paper
to try and score some
sweet scholarship money.
The minute that dough paid out,
I forgot every word
I had written!
[DEANA] I reject this! I won't
entertain the possibility
that you're not a moron!
It's gonna take me quite some
time to adjust to the idea, too.
Then keep telling yourself
whatever you need
to feel better. Oh, question.
I can't seem to figure out
exactly what they put
in the anti-AMS bullets.
Any leads there?
I dunno.
That's highly classified
military intel.
Ah, well, that's a bummer.
Hey, are these the only other
papers we have access to?
Kirill, wait a sec.
Yuri's still in there.
[KIRILL gasps]
[APPLE] She's undergoing
routine maintenance.
Should be wrapping up
any minute now.
What? Maintenance? Come on,
it's not like she's a real
robot or anything like that!
Whoa. So, she's, like, totally
naked in there right now?
It's prob'ly best
you don't look.
It's nothing like what you
might imagine, I promise.
[door creaking]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Were you spying on your
naked subordinate in there?
What? No, no, no!
Oh, did the sight
get you so riled up
you spilled your coffee?
Just forget the whole
thing, all right?
You! Have you finished
those damn reports yet?
Huh?!
[KIRILL]
Jeez! Crap!
[DOUG]
Huh?
[KIRILL]
Uh. What the--?!
[GUS yelps]
Hey, Hold on!
Wait a sec!
Let me go!
You big, dumb loser!
Don't sleep here.
It's super dangerous--
why don't you go on home?
[GUS] 'Cause I don't
have a home, okay?
Can't you just leave
me alone, man?
I'm not a damn criminal!
Go away!
You like this?
Renoir is awesome.
Uh?
I can't die yet.
He still needs me.
I can't leave him.
[JEFFREY gasps]
--[LANDLADY] Oh, I see.
--Huh?
[LANDLADY] I thought
you might swing that way,
but don't you think
he's kinda young?
Ew, gross!
Oh god, no!
What's wrong with you?!
Don't even joke
about that stuff, gah!
[LANDLADY]
Whatever, you have guests!
We brought the Derick's
Special you ordered!
We came all the way out
here to hand deliver it!
Wait, Derick's here, too?
But, why?
He wouldn't let me come alone.
Said women should always
have an escort at night.
[POCHI meows]
[GUS]
We got evicted.
They kicked us out
for missing rent.
Does your dad know?
That you don't have
the money to pay it?
Well, I had the money.
He set up an account
for me to pay rent
and other things that I need.
But that's all gone now.
I had to use it
for his treatments.
Yet you're still flashing
wads of cash to pick up girls.
No, what was-- I wanted...
Uh.
On the day I was born,
my mom passed away.
After she died, Dad just
worked and took care of me.
He never did anything
to have fun or let loose.
[DERICK whimpers]
[GUS]
So, I was doing it for him.
I wanted him to spend time with
a pretty girl before he died.
Otherwise his life would
seem so empty and sad.
And if that was the case, I
could never live with the guilt.
So you did all that
stuff for your dad?
[LANDLADY]
Come on, big guy,
why don't you lend me
a hand in the kitchen?
The least I can do
for that poor kid
is offer him a nice pot
of after-dinner tea.
What is it?
[KIRILL] You don't get
to make that call, kid!
You can't decide
whether your dad's life
was worthwhile or not!
How do you think
he'd feel if he knew
that's what his own
son thought of him?
That'd be even more painful!
Kirill...
Who cares if you've got
money, or girls like you,
or you've got an easy
life. He's got you.
Sure, life is smoother
with that stuff.
But, still, that's not
what's important!
Even if he has to leave you.
Knowing his son's alive
and well because of him?
That is a life well-lived!
So, you have reason to smile,
and celebrate your dad's
life for what it is.
You owe it to him to take care
of yourself and be happy.
What the--?
[snores]
Guess my lecture
put him to sleep.
[MILLA]
You must have been so lonely.
After Grandpa died.
I'm sorry... for leaving
you alone so long.
I already forgave you.
I'm glad we're together now.
[phone rings]
Yeah? Kirill speaking.
Huh? How did that happen?
Fine, whatever, I'm on my way.
Listen.
Think you could look after him?
Yo.
What the hell, man?
Idiot! Why would you
leave the hospital?
Don't you ever
wanna get better?!
You bring the forensics kit?
Don't ignore my reprimand!
[DOUG]
That guy--he's in Overdrive.
Why do I even bother with you?
[KIRILL] Which guy?
The baldy with the sandwich?
What? My scanner's not working.
So that's it.
Will you stop being
so cryptic and explain?
Damn! Dude, wait up!
[DOUG] That same guy was
knocking on death's door
in the hospital this afternoon.
The girls are on
this case, right.
[DOUG gasps]
[KIRILL] Several patients have
checked out of that hospital
on their own only to end up dead
not long after from
Anthem overdose.
This has got to be related.
[DOUG gasps]
You. I saw you at the hospital.
[gasps] Drop the knife,
let's talk!
[PATIENT 10A] There's nothing
for us to talk about.
[KIRILL] I'm warning you!
Drop it, or I'll shoot!
I needed the light of hope!
And I found it in that hospital.
But I need more, dammit!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
Just stay still.
You need a doctor.
Look, I only ever did
what they told me to!
[KIRILL]
Wait!
Shit!
Now, let me see the kit.
[DOCTOR HOPE]
He declined treatment.
Said he was finished and left.
Walked out without a word.
[KIRILL] But, then,
there was another patient
at this hospital who--
Correction, a former patient.
Pardon me, Doctor.
May I ask your opinion,
you being an esteemed
medical professional?
Yes, what is it?
We found Anthem in
the patient's blood.
Do you have any idea how
that might have happened?
He fled the scene in spite
of some nasty wounds,
not to mention his illness.
It seems clear that his body
has undergone some sort of
physical change, yet our systems
didn't detect Overdrive.
I'm just wondering what you
make of that, Doctor.
There's not enough information
to make anything of it.
Although... When you're at
death's door and you feel like
a shell of your former self,
don't you think it's normal
to seek relief in whatever
form you can find it?
Yes, but... Anthem?
[DOCTOR HOPE]
Now please leave.
[DOUG] We should talk with
Travis about this tomorrow,
probably not enough
for a warrant, though.
And I'll fill out those
reports. Eventually.
If Anthem had been developed
for medicinal use from
the very beginning,
do you think things
would be different?
Better, even?
Rich men make that call.
Whether a drug is
poison or a cure.
I think it's up to those
who use it, in the end.
[KIRILL yelps]
You have to tell me what's
happening to my body!
I'm bleeding, but it
doesn't even hurt!
My senses are failing--
I can't taste or smell.
Help me!
I'm still getting
an error message!
I can't feel heat or
cold or anything!
Please! Tell me what's
happening to me!
If you'll take me to the
person who offered you
the light of hope,
we can help you.
We'll find the answers you seek.
Derick? Where's Gus?
[GUS]
Dad, it's me! Huh? Huh?!
He can't be--!
[PATIENT 10A] I just want
to feel something again!
[KIRILL]
He's fast!
There is nothing
for you to fear.
If you take this medicine,
you will find the light of hope.
Isn't there a 30% chance
that takin' it'll kill me?
And the side effects--
aren't they substantial?
[DOCTOR HOPE]
We'll monitor you for 24 hours
and hopefully none
of that will happen.
If you can just make it
through the initial phase,
you'll be free.
Look, Jeffrey. At this rate,
you've only got ten days left
to live, if even that long.
[JEFFREY gasping]
Is that true?
The decision is yours alone.
[JEFFREY gasping]
[footsteps]
[PATIENT 10A grunts]
[JEFFREY gasps]
What's happening to me?
My body is failing!
The loser's here?
Whoa, Gus?
[PATIENT 10A]
Doctor!
Now just relax.
This medicine will
make you feel better.
I asked you a question, dammit!
What the--? Whoa.
[PATIENTS groaning]
[DOUG] Their influence spreads
even further than I thought.
[KIRILL]
Esperanza?!
Their goal must be to figure
out the proper ratios
for the anti-AMS bullets.
[DOUG] They're injecting
patients with Anthem,
then injecting them with
the drugs in the bullets
in different proportions
to find out what works.
They're using
these men as lab rats.
Then those error messages
I was getting...
They must be a result of
the drugs partially working.
Each one of those five drugs
is deadly on its own.
The patient's good
for data, but then...
It's a necessary sacrifice!
If we can attain the benefits of
Anthem without the risks, then,
think of the medical potential!
[PATIENT 10A]
Give me more Anthem, now!
[DOCTOR HOPE]
What are you doing? Stop!
[PATIENT 10A]
I'll test the medical potential!
--[KIRILL gasps]
--No, don't!
Vitality!
Vitality this!
[PATIENT 10A groans]
It hurts.
You have to save me!
Please save me. It... hurts...
[DOCTOR HOPE] He's nothing
more than an animated corpse
awaiting death. And you are
to blame for his suffering!
Your coming here shortened his
life and drove him to the edge!
Save me. I don't want to die.
I'm giving my patients hope
in the face of imminent doom!
[KIRILL] Don't you dare talk
about hope! Shut your mouth!
Enough, let him go.
Jeffery. Do you want to live?
[gasps]
Yes? Then you have to help me!
Use the Anthem, now!
If you take the drug, you'll
have the strength of a giant!
And the vitality to
beat your illness!
[KIRILL]
You liar!
[DOCTOR HOPE]
Come, let's run away.
I'm the only person in the
world who can keep you alive.
[DOCTOR HOPE] Don't you
want to see him grow up?
To see your son get married?
Meet your future grandkids?
I do.
Dad, stop it.
Use it!
No! Don't!
[yells]
[DOCTOR HOPE gasps]
I refuse.
You'll never make me a monster.
I'd rather die as
my son's father.
[DOUG]
Hello, Jeffrey.
How are you doing?
Much better, thanks.
Especially now that I'm
in this fancy new room.
Listen, the investigators will
be asking you some questions.
But, all told, it shouldn't
take more than an hour.
Yes, of course.
There's something else.
Gus planned a special
surprise for you.
What's all this?
You wanted to see
me get married.
So, I am. Well, not really,
but I think you get it.
You look gorgeous.
Yes. I think so, too.
Detective.
I promise to do my best, Dad.
I'm gonna study hard,
and I won't become a thug!
Someday I'll marry for real.
Maybe a pretty girl,
or an ugly one, or heck,
even a guy, like this loser.
Hey, you shouldn't call
your bride a loser!
And who knows? Maybe I
won't even get married at all.
But... If I do,
I want to have a kid.
So, I can be an amazing
father, like you've been.
I'll live like you, for my kid.
But I know I'll be okay
no matter what happens!
So, please, don't just hang on
'cause you're worried about me.
I'm fine, and I'm glad
you're still here--
[GUS, JEFFREY crying]
[KAY]
Interesting.
So, then, Gus is going to live
with your landlady now?
Yeah, but it's just temporary.
In the meantime, they'll
talk to a social worker,
and try to figure out
what comes next.
Are you gonna handle
all that paperwork?
Yeah.
They asked if I wanted
to take him in,
but I don't think I'm ready
for that kind of thing.
Uh! Here, lemme help you.
Thanks, Kirill.
When your shift is over, I'll
walk you home, just to be safe.
And I'll walk you down
the aisle at your wedding!
Well, just because I
wear women's clothes...
Thanks... Little Brother.
[COOPER]
Constable Kirill Vrubel, is it?
[KIRILL, MILLA gasp]
They told me down at the station
that I might find you here.
So... Have any interest
in joining the military?
[NARRATOR] Kirill doesn't know
how to respond
to this sudden invitation!
As the wheels of fate
begin turning faster,
the ball of destiny
starts rolling, too!
Life's a roller coaster,
mother [bleep],
so Kirill better
hold on to his butt!
Next time, on Double Decker :
Episode Eleven!
"SEVEN-O Dies Twice!"
Wait, they can't die!