[HOSPITAL STAFF 4A]
Say cheese!
[DERICK]
Cheese!
[HOSPITAL STAFF 4A]
This hospital's gonna feel
so much less lively
without you around!
I hope you get shot again
so you can come back!
[KIRILL]
Wha--?!
Whoa, whoa. What the heck?!
I thought Derick died
during the investigation!
Sorry.
You thought what? That he died?
Who said it? I-I think...
[DOUG] Thanks to him, one
of our undercover officers
got set up during
an investigation.
[APPLE] It's sad to think I'll
never see them in action again.
[gasps]
[KIRILL]
Nobody actually said it!
So, when he comes back,
what'll happen to me?
[DERICK laughs]
[DERICK] You kidding? I
ain't never comin' back!
I've finally got my
dream job. Why would I?
I've wanted to be a bartender
ever since I was a little kid.
Ya dig?
Dolin' out whatever
poison the people pick.
[NARRATOR] This concludes our
installment of "Derick Returns!"
Oh, right!
This ain't a story
about a detective
who realizes his dreams of
becoming a bartender!
It's about the people who are
livin' the detective dream!
And in this thrilling episode...
[NARRATOR] You'll get the
story of Max. AKA, "Boxer."
NARRATOR A]
Yuri. AKA "Robot."
[NARRATOR]
Kay, alias "Rookie."
And the rest of the lovely
ladies in SEVEN-O,
or, "Travis' Angels," as
everyone in the office
likes to call them!
[DEANA]
Huh?!
I pity the fool who calls us
something that stupid!
[gasps]
I will... end you!
[NARRATOR A]
Can't forget Deana! AKA, "Pink"!
[TRAVIS] Well, it's been
three weeks, now.
Uh. Since the department-wide
reorg, that is.
And, I've received a request
that more visibility
be given to Pink and Rookie.
From above.
Who is "above," exactly?
[coughs]
All right, this time, you'll
be investigating a club
known around town for
its handsome staff.
Thank me later, ladies.
Right! I'll do my best!
[TRAVIS]
Great attitude, Rookie!
[MAXINE sighs]
I guess even low-level
street dealers
are peddling Anthem
these days, aren't they?
Yeah, after what we
saw at the factory,
I'm not ruling anyone out.
[TRAVIS]
That's the right angle,
but until we've got proof,
you better keep digging.
Sophie was good enough to use
her feminine wiles
to get this intel,
but the case is in the Drug
Control Division's Jurisdiction.
Whatever you do, make
sure you don't interfere
with the work they've done.
[KAY]
Right!
That was for you, Pink.
I know how you can be--
[DEANA]
Yeah, yeah. Come on.
[KAY]
Uh, sure!
[door closes]
I don't know why I bother.
Hey. What is he talking about?
[DOUG] Oh. He just wants us to
respect our fellow officers.
[NARRATOR]
Allow me to explain!
SEVEN-O jurisdiction
solely covers crimes
that involve the substance
called "Anthem."
The Drug Control Division
handles crimes
connected to
regular street drugs.
In theory, the departments are
two arms of the same body,
but you try telling them that
when they're vying
for the same case!
Indeed, and that's why
we need to be careful.
Right.
[DEANA]
Hey, you ready to get on this?
Uh. Yes.
Whoa! Why in the world
are you wearing that get-up?
I think you stole
my line, honey.
What the hell are you wearing?
Whatever. You'll be
my naïve little sister.
And you just moved
here from BFE.
Hey! Wait a second!
[ALL] Hey, babes.
Welcome to Train Spotter!
You're such a cutie!
Right back at'cha.
You wanna drink?
[STRIPPER 4B]
Do I ever!
Um, excuse me, could I get a--?
Nope, she's still in diapers,
no booze for her tonight, buddy.
[BARTENDER 4A]
Oh. I forgot, I gotta go.
[KAY] Hey, Deana. Do we
have the money for this?
Yeah. I borrowed some
from Sophie.
Uh. Sophie, my love.
Did you, uh, happen to
swipe my wallet again?
Who, me?
[laughs]
Of course not.
Hell to the yeah!
You mean I'm really
allowed to do this?
You're the best
patron ever, lady!
[DEANA laughs]
There's more where
that came from!
[STRIPPER 4C]
Yeah, I'm down, bring it on!
Stay right here!
Hey, um, aren't we
supposed to be a little bit
more inconspicuous in an
investigation like this?
Rookie, big bait
catches big fish.
I just think we--
Look, if you even dream about
half-assing this thing,
you're gonna end up
on the menu, got it?
Heads up. There's an idiot
at your three o'clock.
I love seein' big spenders
like you goin' all out.
[DEANA] I hope for your sake
you've really got the good stuff
like you say you
do, buddy.
[DRUG PEDDLER 4A] Of course,
whatever you ladies need, I got.
It's the purest stuff in town--
it'll send you
straight to heaven.
You might be going
there first, hon.
What a letdown. You'd better
not be holding out on me.
Where's the Anthem, hottie?
Fine. We'll just take you down
to HQ and make you talk.
[KAY]
Huh? Hey! We can't do that!
This is out of our jurisdiction!
Huh? He's got contraband.
All that stuff's
illegal as hell!
But that falls under the Drug
Control Division's purview,
and not ours, you know that!
We don't have the authorization!
We need to go through
the proper channels.
[DEANA] Keep your
eyes on him, dumbass!
[DEANA]
Stop! Freeze, or I'll shoot!
[KAY]
You can't!
[DEANA]
What's your freakin' problem?
[KAY yelps]
[gasps]
Shit!
He got away because
of you. Happy now?
I'm sorry, but there's protocol.
Apologies don't
bring in criminals.
Even so, rules are rules!
We didn't even have
the right to arrest him.
It was out of our jurisdiction!
[DEANA]
Those are...
[OLD MAN 4A] What are they
fighting about?
From what I can gather,
they let some guy
give them the slip.
If I was their man, I'd be
running the hell away, too.
Can it, geriatric turds!
Responsibility?!
Well, this screw-up is your
responsibility, Rookie.
I'm sorry, I--
I'm willing to ignore the
fact that you're useless.
But, look,
like hell am I gonna let you
mess with my game here!
I've got my own way
of handling things!
Ugh!
[DOUG] Your position's
not wrong, technically.
[KAY] Yeah, but, she's not here,
so she must be super mad.
Did she tell you about it?
"Thank you all for being here.
I am honored to have joined
your ranks, and I hope..."
We bugging you?
[KIRILL]
No, just practicing my speech.
[MAXINE] Well, I'm sorry
your welcome party
turned out to be such a lame
one, that really sucks.
But don't take it personally.
Huh?!
[DOUG] Listen, you don't really
have to make a speech.
[DOUG laughing]
[KIRILL growls]
[KAY]
We're just not a good fit!
She and I are
complete opposites.
[KIRILL]
Huh...?
And I'm not just takin'
about what happened today.
'Cause, like, last time.
[DEANA]
Doug! Lotz confirmed it.
The bastard gave Anthem to Glen,
the prisoner who
started the riot.
He's crying now and
spilling his guts.
Now, sweet stuff,
let's hear what else
you've got to tell us.
And what's up with her
slutty outfit, anyway?
It's a damn dress
code violation!
[MAXINE]
Yeah, but, so what?
It's Travis that lets
her get away with it.
She is one of "Travis'
Angels," after all.
[DOUG]
Let her wear what she wants.
Sometimes that's what
dangerous sting work calls for.
She volunteered to
do undercover stuff,
in exchange for not
getting a partner.
She's spent a lot of
time figuring out
how to survive in that scene.
The clothes are part
of her system.
[DEANA]
Look, if you even dream about
half-assing this thing,
you're gonna end up
on the menu, got it?
Huh? You're allowed to
decline having a partner?
If you're as talented
as she is, yeah.
I'm confused.
Why did Deana agree to
work with Kay, then?
It's weird.
She turned down everyone
else, but took you on.
[KAY] I heard I was a
replacement for somebody else,
so maybe that's what happened.
If you mean Jefferson,
he was just some guy
that Travis forced on us.
So, then, why did she
agree to work with me?
Maybe you've got some quality
she knows she lacks.
Something she thought
would help her.
Okay!
I'm gonna stick it out with
her a little bit longer,
keep doing my best,
and see what happens.
And I'll take full
responsibility for everything
that went down with
the botched sting today.
Huh?!
[KIRILL] Responsibility?
You sure about that?
I am.
And I have an idea
that just might work.
[DEANA] "Responsibility?"
Responsibility for what?!
Please! What's the problem
with hanging a suspect
upside down for questioning?!
Come on, it's unethical!
Due process and all
that, you know?
[DEANA] Screw those
bleeding heart rules!
Are we children?!
It's not like this
is anything new.
We're a special breed.
We're detectives,
but we're also in constant
danger of being disavowed
and shut down by men
who sit behind desks.
We're kind of like
spies, in a way.
That's why Travis is so adamant
about everyone havin' a partner.
He thinks it's a sort
of insurance plan,
a way to keep us safe out
in the field, and I agree.
It works. The Double
Decker system.
[DEANA]
Ugh, enough. Cringe worthy.
You know it's a good
idea, just admit it.
[DEANA blows raspberry]
[DERICK] And it's not without
additional perks, too.
You can do half the work
and get twice the credit.
[DEANA]
Even with a prissy
goody-two-shoes
partner like her?
[DERICK] I think she's exactly
the type of sidekick you need.
A perfect foil for you.
[DEANA] It's a whole lot
faster if we go this way.
Don't be such a scaredy-cat!
[sighs] To find the fastest
route from point A to point B,
it's better if you
just go it alone.
Hey, Derick?
[DERICK]
Hm?
[DEANA]
It's bugging me.
Why'd you really quit the force?
[DERICK] Hm. Honestly,
it really wasn't anything
too big or dramatic.
That's about the size of it.
[DEANA laughs]
So stupid,
but you sure had me freaked
out for a second there.
Uh!
Although, I am
relieved it wasn't
because of the whole
Esperanza thing.
Thanks. I guess.
[DEANA] You're a dog lover,
aren't you, D?
This is for you.
[DERICK gasping]
[DEANA] I made it yesterday.
It's a bar-warming gift.
[DERICK]
Uh?
[GARY]
So, you got it, huh?
The rookie spot in SEVEN-O.
Well, I'm proud that it's
one of my students, at least.
Your good grades paid off.
I've always wanted to work
over there, truth be told.
So, uh, sir?
About the narcotics
seized yesterday.
Of course.
The lab tests found
illegal compounds.
I thought they would.
I was right.
Why don't you take us
to that club now.
We'll launch our
own investigation
and corroborate your intel.
It's protocol, don't worry.
I'm sorry.
I know it's weird,
coming to you.
It's not weird at all,
kid, no sweat.
I'll be sure to set
things up so nobody ends up
stepping on anybody else's toes.
The most important
thing to remember
in any undercover operation
is to always act naturally.
[gasps] That's the guy.
Let's go, then.
Sometimes it pays off
to be a little bold.
I knew it, Anthem!
Right. Whelp, sorry,
this is a trap.
[KAY]
Huh? [screams]
[KAY groans]
Being bold almost
never pays off.
And you've failed
me as a student.
So naive.
[DEANA] I'm in the middle
of something, Max.
Make it quick.
Huh? Fine, I'll call
you back in a bit.
So, show me the body.
[MALE COP 4A]
Right this way.
[GARY]
You seem confused.
You still don't
get what this is?
Why don't you tell me?
Well, for starters,
let me just say it's
got nothing to do
with you and your buddies
over at SEVEN-O.
And this isn't even Anthem.
It's a decoy, a stimulant.
Not easy to differentiate
from the real thing, huh?
I've got a rockin' side gig,
selling what we confiscate.
[KAY gasping]
Now, a pop quiz.
Can you tell me what the
fatality rate for Anthem is?
Around 30%.
[GARY]
Correct.
You've kept up your
homework, I see.
Anthem is the deadliest drug
out there, as you know.
But that doesn't stop people
from lining up to buy it.
It's just too enticing
to resist.
[KAY]
Why are you telling me this?
You haven't figured it out?
[DEANA]
I'll run an analysis at HQ
and report back immediately
if he tests positive for Anthem.
[gasps]
We've used this Anthem
craze to our advantage.
Most of the sad sacks
who seek us out
to buy it leave with
poison instead.
But the special ones, the
ones we don't want to kill?
We give them stimulants.
And I get to choose who's
special and who isn't.
The ones who survive believe
they've been chosen
by the Anthem,
like some kind of
elite secret society.
Thus, the rumors spread,
and demand for the product
increases exponentially.
That's terrible.
Terrible?
But the only victims
of my clever ruse
are the low-lifes trying
to score Anthem!
If anything, you and
all your silly cohorts
at SEVEN-O should
be thanking me.
[door clicks]
[DRUG PEDDLER 4A] This business
we're in is treacherous,
full of dangers at every turn.
Take a look at who we just
found sniffing around outside.
We're sorry, Kay.
Kirill and I got
worried about you,
so we decided to
follow you over here.
Well, this is lucky.
Couldn't've planned it better.
We were thinking it was time
we got out of this business,
but you showing up here
changes everything.
Now there's an even more
lucrative opportunity available.
And what would that be?
You'll have your colleagues
bring a sample of the drug
used in Anti-AMS bullets.
[KAY]
Huh?
[GARY]
That precious magic ammo
is the one reliable
way to fight Anthem.
So, a sample of the
compound it contains
would be worth a fortune
to the right people.
I won't! No way!
[DRUG PEDDLER 4A] Do what we
say, or we'll kill the girl.
And as for the boy?
He'll die slowly.
Wait, why do I
have to die slowly?!
[GARY]
Make your choice.
Your plan wouldn't work.
No one at SEVEN-O would bring
you something so crucial!
I know one person who would.
[DEANA]
Jeez.
You sure are asking a lot
of me with this, you know?
That said, using this
stuff to lure Esperanza
right into our hands
isn't a bad idea.
[KAY] As it turns out,
that dealer, James,
really was selling
Anthem out of the club.
My instincts were right.
That place reeked of depravity.
I'm certain that James guy's
working for Esperanza.
It makes perfect sense.
As soon as he's got a sample,
I predict that he'll lead
us right to the big boss.
Yeah, I agree.
This stuff would be a
game changer for them,
and they'd kill to get
their hands on it.
Our lovely Kay, here,
has graciously
volunteered to let James
swipe the bait from her.
[DEANA]
That's perfect, then.
The bigger the payload,
the better.
Call me as soon as you
make contact with him.
I had no doubt that you'd be
willing to help us with this.
[KAY whimpers]
You seem to be doing well, Gary.
Yeah, so do you, D.
[gasps] Deana!
[DEANA grunts]
[KAY groans]
[gasps]
[laughing]
Esperanza approached
Deana del Rio
and offered her a deal
she couldn't refuse.
When she arrived at the
agreed meeting place,
they ambushed her and made
off with the drug sample,
or so the report will say.
You lied to me!
That wasn't the plan!
[GARY]
The plan, huh?
Did you really expect me
to keep my word?
[DEANA]
He's right, Rookie.
[gasps]
[DEANA]
How naive can you be?
Still think it's outside
our jurisdiction?
Well... Technically, yeah.
We've got cause to claim
self-defense, now.
Freeze, asshole!
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Looks like he wants
to play chase.
What's the matter,
does baby need a nap?
No way.
That's Anthem!
[ANTHEM]
Justice!
[ANTHEM laughing]
How wonderful,
it seems I've been
chosen by the gods!
[ANTHEM] I wasn't special
enough for SEVEN-O,
but I have this!
Why would they ever
pick someone like you?
Hold on, he's just jealous?
He's in Overdrive!
Stupid!
[ANTHEM]
Come out, now, Deana del Rio!
If you apologize for
humiliating me,
I'll let her live.
[DEANA grunts]
Do you think they're
gonna be okay?
Deana will be all right.
Not sure about Kay, though.
[ANTHEM] Drop the gun, and
kneel before me in worship!
[ANTHEM] Oh, so you will
sacrifice your pride
to save your partner?
I didn't think you
had it in you!
[gasps]
You misunderstand her.
This isn't for me.
She'd never bother.
She'll take the shortest route
and run it as fast as she can.
[ANTHEM groans]
[ANTHEM] You mean, you'd
just let your partner die?
You're supposed to save
her, no matter what!
You dummy, don't you know
that I never make mistakes?
I'm a freakin' saint,
you got that?
You've caught a nasty bug.
Now, take your medicine.
[ANTHEM screams]
Hey, Gary. Everything
go as planned?
[DEANA]
Sorry, Gary's all tied up.
See what I mean?
I told you Deana'd be all right.
[gasps]
[YURI] Now activating
backup motors and linking
feedback to actuators
28.9% until criticality.
[gasps]
Huh?!
--Uh?!
--[engine revs]
SEVEN-O, here.
Did you really believe
we were hostages?
Come on, are you kidding?
I was just trying to
keep you busy, girl.
[exhales]
[KIRILL]
So, this is why Deana told us
not to take our eyes off Kay.
And these two. Travis's Angels.
Wait, why are you
even here, exactly?
[KIRILL] Huh? Oh, Doug thought I
should come along for the ride.
He said it would be a learning
opportunity for the two of us.
Hold on. Where
is Doug, anyway?
[DEANA] Looks like these
guys are all done here.
How'd you know
it was a set-up?
[DEANA] Yuri told me that you
had gone back to the club
with a detective from
the Drug Control Division.
Max caught on pretty fast.
Then, when I found
out it was Gary--
I told them not to take
their eyes off you.
That guy... We used to work
together back in the day.
He had a stellar record,
but there was something
off about him.
When the position at
SEVEN-O opened up,
Gary was the first to apply.
But, then...
[ANTHEM] Why would they ever
pick someone like you?
[DEANA] Travis said Gary
was too attached
to his sense of right and wrong.
[KAY]
Deana? Is it always like this?
[DEANA]
Yeah.
It's just my way of doing
things. Don't like it--
[KAY] I want you to teach me
everything you know!
Huh?
[KAY] But the rules
are still the rules,
and I won't compromise on that!
Here I thought you only
had the same name
as my former partner,
but you've got the
same personality.
[KAY]
Huh? Partner?
When was this?
Why didn't I hear
about it before now?
I don't think that's any of
your business, now, is it?
[DEANA]
It's not a big deal!
Why do you hafta be
such a worry wart, Kay?
Ha!
[MAXINE] I think she's
talking about a dog.
Huh?
I mean,
I'm pretty sure Deana's
old dog was named Kay.
That's why she jumped
at the chance
to take Rookie on.
A dog?
[DEANA]
What are you doing? Come on!
Uh. Coming!
Slow ass.
[KAY]
I'm sorry.
Hey. Bark like a dog for me.
[KAY]
No, way, weirdo!
Seems like they'll make
a good team after all.
Sometimes opposites do attract.
Yeah. And him? How's
that been working out?
[DOUG]
Hm?
[growling]
Why didn't you come
save me, Doug?
We're supposed to be a team!
Oh, I figured you'd be
okay with Yuri there.
I turned out to be right, too.
So rude.
Oh, I forgot! Yuri!
Listen, don't tell anybody
I said this, but...
About Yuri. I think... she
might actually be a robot.
[NARRATOR] It's public
knowledge that Yuri is,
indeed, actually a robot.
However...
[DOUG]
No way. That's impossible!
[KIRILL] I don't have
definitive proof yet,
so don't spread it around.
Got it. I won't tell a soul.
[NARRATOR]
That's right!
Doug is, indeed,
actually an asshole!
[DOUG] I'll keep an
eye out for evidence.
[KIRILL] Thanks.
You're the best, partner!
[NARRATOR A] Now that
you've learned that Doug
is a big-time asshole, you
know pretty much everything
you'd ever need to know about
the characters in this story.
Good! Now things
can really get moving!
Next time, on Double Decker !
Episode five: "A. Kroyd Killer!"
Don't be late, jerks!