[KIRILL]
Hey, don't worry.
Morgan can be trusted.
[DOUG] I'm not saying
that I don't believe you.
Let's go.
[KIRILL] Now's my chance
to become a hero!
This is SEVEN-O!
[NARRATOR]
For those of you just tuning in,
allow me to explain.
That's a woman.
Just kidding. He's a man!
And this is a story
about heroes.
Just kidding. It's not!
It's a story about detectives,
who wouldn't have jobs if it
weren't for your tax dollars!
[KIRILL] About a week before
the events you just witnessed,
I became a detective and
received my first codename,
and my second.
[KIRILL] I'd taken my first step
toward becoming a hero, when...
[TRAVIS]
I'm sorry, Okappa.
But you're fired.
[gasps]
[KIRILL] The next day,
everything fell apart.
[KIRILL]
W-Wait. I-I don't understand.
What did I do wrong?
I made a mistake.
We had one open slot, not two.
And unfortunately, that
position was meant for Kay.
So, you were never really
supposed to be here.
Huh?!
[TRAVIS]
I'm sorry, Okappa.
It's not going to work out.
Maybe your old job's
still open, though.
Come on! You can't be serious
right now. I just--
[TRAVIS] The real victim
in all this is me.
I'm not saying that you
aren't suffering too, but
a mistake like this will very
likely cost me a promotion.
Sorry again!
[gasping]
[NARRATOR] As he absorbed his
erstwhile supervisor's less
than diplomatic words,
Kirill thought to himself:
[KIRILL]
"I know! This must be a trial
laid out for me by the
god of heroes himself!"
I understand now, sir.
[TRAVIS]
Hm?
I'd like you to give
me one week.
If I can't accomplish
anything during that time,
I'll gladly leave.
You won't see me again.
However, if I do manage
to prove myself,
I want you to consider keeping
me here in SEVEN-O.
Surely your bosses can be
persuaded to add a slot.
[NARRATOR]
That's right!
He's an idiot!
[NARRATOR]
Too late, Kirill realized,
there was no way his boss
would accept this proposal.
Why would he? There was
nothing in it for him.
But then...
Mm... Fine. If you manage
to impress me,
I'll consider it.
[NARRATOR]
That's right!
Travis Murphy is also an idiot.
Great, another moron
to deal with.
Can't you do something?
I think he looks fun. You don't?
[KIRILL] "All I need is
one crime and I'll be able
to keep my end of
the deal. Easy."
Or so I thought.
But, then...
Where did all the crime go?
Meetings, paperwork, training,
paperwork, overtime, paperwork.
I thought a detective's
job would be exciting,
full of action. Not just
a bunch of boring deskwork.
And when we did
get called out...
Honestly, how could you
be such a total moron?
The only moron here is you!
[KIRILL] It was just
boring surveillance
for Phase One undercover
investigations.
[COUPLE shouting]
[KIRILL]
And this Doug guy...
He's impossible to figure out.
I have no idea what's
going through his head.
Is he really the same person?
Hey, it's just two boyfriends
screaming at each other
and throwing stuff.
This is pointless.
All right.
Let's take them off the list
and see what else we have.
[gasps] How about him?
I mean, check out
that moustache.
He totally looks evil.
Can't. Deana's already
going after him.
[grunts]
[KIRILL]
No luck.
Nothing's looking
promising so far.
Ugh! I've only got
two days left.
I've always found that the more
desperate a man is for a win,
the sloppier he's likely to get.
Who're you?
Have you really played all
the cards in your hand?
[KIRILL]
Um, what?
I... [gasps]
That's it!
That's just what I
needed to hear!
Thank you, random man in a bar!
[KIRILL]
Propelled by a cryptic statement
from a man I'd never met,
I went in search of an
informant named Morgan.
Hey, there.
Been awhile, Morgan. What's up?
So, you're a detective now, kid?
Yeah. Got any good info for me?
Well, funny you should
ask, actually.
Remember Billy
the Coin Collector,
that petty thief you picked
up a while ago?
[gasps]
Seems he just got out,
and he's been goin' around
braggin' about some big
job he's got coming up.
Yeah? So what's the job, then?
[MORGAN]
This one's on the house.
Rumor goin' around is that
Anthem's involved somehow.
[KIRILL gasps]
So this guy's smuggling Anthem.
Are you sure about this?
Yes! In all the time
I've used him,
Morgan's never
given me bad info.
[KIRILL]
Figures.
I can tell what he's thinking.
He's got a look on his face
like he's trying to come up
with some way to get out
of following this lead.
But I'm not backing down.
I don't care what the thinks--
Huh. Anyone ever tell you
your face looks like a girl's?
Huh?!
All right. Let's go.
[KIRILL]
Uh? Uh, right.
Heh!
[KIRILL] And so, I got what
was probably my last chance
to become a hero.
As far as I know, Billy's
got no family to speak of.
He's out of prison now,
but with zero connections,
he doesn't have a lot of
options for making money.
It's no wonder he'd turn
to Anthem smuggling.
I see. Makes sense.
Anthem's really dangerous stuff.
It must sell for a lot
to the right buyer.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, don't worry.
Morgan can be trusted.
I'm not saying that
I don't believe you.
[KIRILL]
Hmph.
What?
You don't wanna go in
there unarmed, do you?
[gasps]
Who's Derick?
Let's go.
Freeze! SEVEN-O!
All right, everyone,
hands behind your head,
and hands on the floor!
[SMUGGLER 2A]
Uh. Hold on a sec.
[SMUGGLER 2B]
How would that even work?
You have to pick one.
They can't do both.
[KIRILL gasps]
[SMUGGLER 2A groans]
[SMUGGLER 2B]
Can't do it!
This is where you're
hiding the Anthem, huh?
[SMUGGLER 2A]
Ugh, my back.
[KIRILL]
Hmph.
[MONKEYS chirp]
[KIRILL]
Monkeys...? Uh....
[chirping]
[DOUG] Thank you for
your cooperation.
As you can see, this was
a training exercise.
We appreciate your help.
[KIRILL grunts]
Where's the pep talk?
[DOUG]
Hm?
"Don't let it get you down."
"Everybody makes mistakes."
You know. That sort of thing.
Yeah. Your idea that
he'd gotten involved
in Anthem smuggling
made sense.
[DOUG] Anthem's gotten
incredibly popular
in the last few years.
And since it's so much riskier
to handle than other drugs,
dealers can make a hell of
a lot of money off of it.
It's an increasingly common
story these days--
someone who's down on their
luck gets into Anthem dealing,
hoping to make a fortune,
only to have it ruin their life.
Huh?
If things had turned
out differently,
then that could have
been my story.
Well, we were orphans.
So, y'know...
Who is "we"?
I grew up with my older
sister, but she disappeared
a decade ago, and I
haven't seen her since.
Not even a trace.
Huh?
That's the whole reason
I became a cop.
Because I wanted
to look for her.
I needed more information,
and that's how I started
working with Morgan.
But, it turns out that this job
isn't exactly what I expected.
I always figured that I
would have more freedom
if I was able to work
my way up to detective.
But now I don't know.
So, what made you decide
to become a cop, anyway?
Look, you don't have
to say, but honestly,
I'd kinda like to know.
[DOUG]
Hm?
Uh. What did you say?
[KIRILL] I told you about why
I wanted to become a cop!
Oh. Anything else?
[KIRILL]
Yeah. I also asked
why you decided to
become a detective!
Ah. No reason, really.
Oh, okay. Guess it's
like that for some people.
No, I had a reason.
What's with you?!
[DOUG] I don't know if it's
why I became a cop, exactly,
but there's something I
want to rid the world of.
Are you talking about Anthem?
[sirens blare]
[radio static]
[SOPHIE]
Attention! Calling all units.
SEVEN-O HQ here.
A riot has broken out at
Desperatio Prison in Ignis Base.
One guard has been wounded.
The man believed to have
incited the riot
is one Henry Glen, who
was serving a life term.
It's possible that Glen had help
from inside the prison system,
but we cannot yet confirm it.
He and several other
prisoners are attempting
to take advantage of the
chaos to make their escape.
The police believe the escapees
are still on the island,
and have sealed Santcus Bridge,
the only way in or out.
All SEVEN-O officers are to be
on standby for more inform--
Billingham here.
You copy, Deana?
Copy, where are you, Doug?
[DOUG] Hey, that guard
you were looking into.
Yeah. His name's Rob Lotz.
And I'm way ahead of you.
[KIRILL]
Rob Lotz?
Yeah. He's the prison guard
that Deana was investigating.
[KIRILL growls]
[KIRILL] Shouldn't we be on
our way to the prison?
Cool your jets.
It's not our jurisdiction.
Seriously?
Nope. If my guess
is right, though--
[DEANA]
Doug! Lotz confirmed it.
The bastard gave Anthem to Glen,
the prisoner who
started the riot.
[DOUG]
Roger.
[gasps]
[KIRILL]
I still don't understand.
How's a drug responsible
for causing a prison riot?
Is Anthem really that dangerous?
[DOUG]
It is. Like any drug,
it gives you a sense of
omnipotence and pleasure,
but what makes it
particularly nasty is that
it removes all your
natural limiters.
That's what you call
"Overdrive," right?
Nope. That's something
else, actually.
Hey, were you planning to
tell me where we're going?
To the crime scene.
Wouldn't that be
the bridge, though?
[DOUG]
Not anymore.
The escapees are probably
off the island by now.
I'm guessing they swam.
And why do you think that?
It's simple, really.
I calculated where you'd
end up if you swam,
based on the tidal currents.
The tides would take you
right to the warehouse
that informant told you about.
He told you it was a job
involving Anthem, didn't he?
Think about it.
Those containers
in the warehouse.
If your guy was right, those
were most likely placed there
to smuggle the prisoners out
after they'd escaped the island.
That makes sense, but it's
a lot of dots to connect.
How'd you know?
Hunch.
That's all?!
Except. There's still something
that's bothering me.
It's the monkeys.
Like?
[DOUG] There were plastic
bottles filled with water
in that container we
opened, remember?
So...
Question is, can a monkey
open a plastic bottle?
I mean, they are pretty
smart, so it's possible.
But what do you think?
Well... They are pretty
smart, so it's possible?
I see. Maybe I'm
overthinking this.
No! You're right!
The monkey thing
is totally weird.
[DOUG]
Totally weird.
[KIRILL gasping]
Are you kidding me?
A bomber.
A robber!
And he's a freakin'
serial killer!
We're looking at
a warehouse full
of infamous criminals,
here! Who is this guy?
[KIRILL] If this is falling
in my lap on my last day,
then luck is really on my side.
That's it. This time
I'm going to--
[DOUG]
We're going back to the car.
[KIRILL]
Go back to the car!
[gasping]
Glen isn't in there.
That's not good.
[KIRILL]
This is insane!
Why are we just
leaving them there?
I put a call in to the police
HQ to let them know.
Don't worry,
they'll take care of it.
[KIRILL]
But what about us?
Our job is to focus
on Anthem cases.
Give me the routes the
ambulances are using
to take the injured from
the prison to the hospital.
[SOPHIE]
Roger.
Here's what I'm thinking.
Glen used the gang at the
warehouse as a decoy,
and chose a simpler and more
certain route to escape.
[KIRILL]
Thanks. Sorry to bother you.
All right, the injured are
definitely prison guards.
I checked their IDs and made
sure their fingerprints matched.
Of course, Glen
could've gotten away,
assuming he transformed
into someone else entirely.
Sorry. Am I free
to go now, or--?
Sure. Go on.
Wait.
You know, you're a handsome guy.
[BOTH gasp]
[DOUG]
Who are you with?
What precinct?
Let me see your ID.
[KIRILL]
Uh...
What the hell is wrong
with you people?
Well, if I can't see your ID,
how about your neck?
[gasps]
[KIRILL]
Hey! Get back here!
Let's go.
[DOUG]
The escaped convict is heading
south on West Magnalupus.
Requesting backup.
Wanna tell me what
the hell's happening?!
It's Overdrive.
Glen went into an
Anthem-induced Overdrive.
Resulting in that handsome face.
That ambulance driver
is the guy we're after?
Why didn't he just escape
with the others?
[DOUG] Since he no longer
looked like himself,
Glen was able to slip away
from the prison unnoticed.
[HENRY]
Handsome!
[sirens blare]
Damn!
[HENRY gasping]
[KIRILL]
Ah! Stop the car! Stop the car!
[DOUG]
See, the thing about Anthem
is that it alters
the human genome.
So, sometimes it can
induce rapid evolution.
That's what we call Overdrive.
Hey! Stop talking!
[DOUG]
We're gonna speed up a bit.
Huh?!
[DOUG] We can assume that
the handsome face he acquired
was intended to provide him
with an evolutionary advantage.
[KIRILL]
More exposition?!
[screams]
[KIRILL]
Uh?
[DOUG]
If you look at it one way,
he was essentially "chosen."
But... Evolution can be a
strange thing, sometimes.
[HENRY]
Save me!
[KIRILL gasps]
Time for your medicine.
[gunshot]
You two okay in there?
[PARAMEDIC 2A gasping]
Is this the hospital?
[DOUG]
Another ambulance is on its way.
Come on out if you can walk.
Here. Let me help.
[KIRILL]
Seriously. Who is this guy?
Damn...
In the end, we only
arrested one person.
And compared to Wonder Boy,
I barely even did
anything to help.
Hey, don't let it get you down.
Let me buy you a drink.
'Kay. You wanna tell
me one more time
why we didn't arrest those
guys in the warehouse?
You're still thinking
about that, huh?
Well, yeah. Of course.
That was my chance to
finally become a hero!
We only have jurisdiction over
cases that involve Anthem.
You know that.
That sounds like an excuse
for running away.
Admit it, you were just scared.
[DOUG]
That's part of it.
[KIRILL]
Huh?
Why are you surprised?
--Of course, I was scared.
--[KIRILL grunts]
You always like this
when you're drunk?
[NEWSCASTER 1A]
All of the escaped prisoners
have been apprehended...
Listen! Unlike you,
I've got aspirations.
I'm gonna be this
city's hero someday.
[DOUG]
Sure. For 15 minutes.
Huh?
Fact is, just about anyone can
be a hero for 15 minutes.
Look.
[NEWSCASTER 1A] And now,
the dog who became a hero.
And by the next day,
everybody's forgotten them.
I'm not saying that
there's anything wrong
with being a hero. But...
...the most daring ones are
always the first to die.
[DOUG] Thanks to him, one
of our undercover officers
got set up during
an investigation.
[DOUG] There's something I
want to rid the world of.
See ya.
[door creaks]
[KIRILL]
Doug!
You became a detective
so you could rid the world
of Anthem, right?
Let me help you,
and we can do it together!
We won't ever be rid of Anthem.
One more person trying
won't change that.
[KIRILL] Okay, so I may not
be able to take the place
of that Derick guy,
but I know that I can
be useful somehow!
That's why you recommended me
for the job at SEVEN-O isn't it?
Please just give me a chance!
Let me be your Double Decker!
[DOUG]
Could you not shout like that?
It's kind of embarrassing.
[sighs] It looks like you
misunderstood me before.
I wasn't talking about Anthem
when I said I wanted to rid
the world of something.
Did you mean crime, then?
Not that, either.
Look, I'm sick of guessing.
What is it?
What are you trying to
erase from the world?
Just tell me!
There're two things.
Which are?
One is poverty.
Oh. Uh...
And class is the other.
Ridding the world
of those things
is why I became a detective.
[gasps]
That's what you want?
Really?
[KIRILL]
Wow!
Those are some
serious ambitions!
[yawns]
[KIRILL]
And so, my week came to an end.
[KIRILL] I didn't accomplish
much of anything,
so I'm probably fired.
Part of me wishes I
could stay on longer.
But strangely,
I don't feel any regrets.
Where's Doug?
Huh. I don't think he's
in yet today, actually.
I see.
[KIRILL] Yes. My time
may have been cut short,
but just meeting the man named
Doug made coming here worth it.
[DEANA]
Hey, Okappa.
Travis wants you in his office.
Right.
[KIRILL]
One lesson he taught me
was more important
than any other.
I don't want to be a 15-minute
hero who's easily forgotten.
I want to be a hero strong
enough to protect my big sister.
This is, uh...?
Well, duh.
This is your uniform and
accessories, obviously.
Huh? I don't understand.
I barely accomplished
anything this past week.
Huh? Oh.
Oh. Yeah, you're right.
But, still. In the end,
I guess it was okay.
[KIRILL gasps]
A lot happened. And, well,
I guess you don't
suck too badly.
Uh, good.
[TRAVIS] Hm... People will
probably think you're a girl
if we keep calling you Okappa.
I know!
From now on, your code
name will be Buzz-Cut!
Hey, Buzz-Cut. Lookin' good.
[KIRILL gasps]
[NARRATOR]
And so, in the end,
I guess Kirill didn't suck too
badly, because he was now an
official member of the Special
Crime Investigation Unit.
Thus, clad in a
shiny new uniform,
Kirill took another step on the
path toward becomin' a hero.
[NARRATOR] Kirill begins his
new life as Detective Buzz-Cut,
and for the first time ever, he
faces the prospect of romance.
Or maybe not, actually.
Double Decker Episode Three:
"Your Rival Is Your
Partner's Partner!"
Don't miss it!