[DERICK] What? You lost
contact with Doug?
Let's stick with the plan.
I'll meet up with the others and
go from there, as discussed.
We're countin' on you.
Get it, girlie.
[KAY grunts]
Well, then, Max?
You seeing any military
reinforcements?
No. We're still
all right, I think.
[KIRILL]
Okay, fine, Cooper.
I give.
You win. I'll come with you.
Very well. Follow me.
[NARRATOR] This is a story
about detectives.
Brave men and women
willing to risk their lives
in the line of duty.
[KIRILL] I thought you were
gonna fire that rocket,
so they could come pick me up.
[COOPER] I have to take care of
some last-minute things first.
[KIRILL]
"Last-minute things?"
[COOPER]
Yes. As I mentioned previously,
this base holds a wealth of
classified military knowledge.
Those secrets must
stay protected.
Of course, a system has
already been put into place
that will erase every one
of them in case of a breach.
In fact, it can
only be activated
in the event that the
facility is overrun,
and not without
my final approval.
Because the activation code
has only been programmed
into my ID card.
All staff on the premises
will get an evacuation order
as soon as the system initiates.
And all the facilities'
self-destruct mechanisms
will be triggered, as well--
causing the whole thing to
blow up in exactly 30 minutes.
Then, just to be thorough,
the military will send in its
high-tech bombers to obliterate
every last trace
of its existence.
You can't...
You're just going to
destroy everything here?
I am, indeed.
There's no longer
any need for all this.
I told you.
The people of Nikai are willing
to destroy entire civilizations
just to get you back.
That's how invaluable
you are to our enquiry.
The antibodies in your blood
will revolutionize our genetic
modification research.
As the man responsible
for bringing you back,
I'll be lauded as a hero
and remembered for
generations to come.
Heh. I was tiring of this
mission, honestly.
Toiling away in obscurity
in the middle of nowhere.
That Billingham's an even
bigger fool than I thought.
To think a man like him would
fall for such a simple ruse.
[KIRILL growls]
Now, then, it's time for me
to go make my report.
[KIRILL grunts]
[MILLA gasps]
[COOPER]
Idiot!
Did you really think I wouldn't
assume that multiple doses
of the antibodies
had been produced?
[MILLA]
No. I knew you would.
[COOPER groans]
[MILLA] Too bad, Cooper,
you let your guard down!
Why... you bastard!
Milla. Get to Derrick
and find the others!
I see. So you really do
want to meet your end.
Yeah. Go right ahead, hero.
But, if you do, know that
you're gonna lose your shot
at fame and glory on Nikai.
[COOPER] I'm willing to
bring back your corpse
if that's what it comes down to.
[heartbeats]
[COOPER gasping]
[KIRILL] Looks like
it's already kicking in.
No matter how this turns out,
you're still finished.
Even if I do die here today,
my friends are gonna arrest you
and make sure you get locked up.
It's kind of funny, actually.
I didn't even have to use
Zabel's special Anthem.
[COOPER gasps]
[KIRILL]
Uh! You won't get away!
[COOPER grunting]
So, that means this stuff is
Zabel's special formula?
Interesting. He tried to
Overdrive with an Anthem
that carries no risk of death,
and achieve the same
level of power I had.
Ha. Perfect.
Now... Reboot!
[COOPER]
Heh.
Now, die!
Ha. Guess I missed you,
but next time I won't.
[KIRILL]
Tch.
[DEANA] You need to do more
core work, Dumbass Buzz-Cut.
[gasps]
Kirill! You okay?
Yeah, I think so.
[COOPER chuckles]
[COOPER laughing]
[gasps]
No matter how many
of you wimps show up,
you will never be able
to defeat me!
[KAY]
Deana!
Good girl, Kay!
[COOPER grunts]
That's checkmate, Cooper.
[gunshots]
[gasps]
You're not half bad.
[COOPER] So, Zabel finally
achieved what we spent
all those years researching.
I must say I'm rather impressed.
The irony is so delicious.
It will be your undoing.
You won't see the
light of another day!
It looks like Doug was right.
Huh?
Underneath it all, you were
just afraid of the power
of my antibodies.
You lived with the fear
that their existence would lead
to the loss of your power.
Tell yourself what you want!
I still win!
[DOUG]
Nope. Got you beat, big guy.
[COOPER]
Huh?
Villains can't resist
jumping at the enemy's bait.
You types never seem to learn.
What's going on here?
[DEANA] You haven't figured
it out, Muscle-brains?
Milla didn't inject you
with what you think.
That was just a
little adrenaline,
not Kirill's antibodies.
It takes time to derive a drug
from antibodies in the blood.
But, luckily for us,
you didn't even consider that.
We tricked you into believing
that you'd lost your power
so you chose to rely on Anthem!
[COOPER growls]
What's this? My body is--
Yeah, too bad you
already used a drug
with the same chemical makeup
as Anthem before doing it again!
[screaming]
[DOUG]
Right.
That's something we
learned about the drug.
If you use multiple doses
in a short period,
you end up completely losing
control of your body.
[COOPER groaning]
[DOUG]
"Special Anthem formula"?
Someone with your
background should know
there's no such thing.
All Zabel gave me
was information.
And access to the Eye System.
[COOPER groaning]
[DOUG] Looks like you've
finally reached Overdrive.
[COOPER]
Just Anthem?
How could I have fallen
for a simple bluff?
[DOUG]
Now I can administer treatment.
[COOPER]
No you won't!
You're just relying on your
power now, I can tell.
You don't see anything.
[KIRILL]
Of course not,
because your power was
all you ever really had!
[DOUG] It's your mental
stumbling block.
[COOPER gasps]
[BOTH]
Time for your medicine.
[gunshot]
[DOUG]
Brian Cooper.
[COOPER panting]
You are under arrest for the
illicit use of the drug Anthem.
Aren't you idiots forgetting
one important detail here?
[DOUG]
Hm?
[KAY]
The bombers!
Ugh. That was a nasty little
idea you dreamed up, buddy.
Indeed. And, as the
commander of this base
I'm the only one
with the authority
to call off the air strike.
Eight hundred fifteen hours.
Per Lisvaletta Penal
Code, article 253,
and effective as of this moment:
All Brian Cooper's official
authority has been suspended
for proven Anthem use,
as well as abuse of power,
and suspected acts of treason
against the Lisvaletta military.
Thus, all his authority
shall pass to his adjutant,
Kirill Vrubel.
Huh?!
[DERICK] Abort the mission.
I repeat, abort the mission!
[APPLE] I sent the photos
exactly as instructed.
He's done.
[DOUG]
That's right.
We had no jurisdiction
when we first came here.
So, to get rid of you,
and do it in a way that
wouldn't get us in trouble,
we needed to get you to
use Anthem in my eye line
and somehow catch
you in the act.
[COOPER growling]
[KIRILL]
U-Uh...
Do we have clearance, adjutant?
Uh, yeah. Also.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Cooper.
[COOPER]
Heh.
[alarm blares]
[KIRILL gasps]
It's time to go! Come on!
Deana! Kay! That sign says
the exit is down this way!
We have no choice.
We can't wait!
But...
[DEANA]
Just shut up and run!
[KIRILL] Uh! What the
hell is going on now?
Once the self-destruct
sequence initiates,
there's no possible way
to stop the devices
from taking their
intended course.
You okay, Constable Vrubel?
I think... I'm all right.
But we might have lost Cooper.
It's fine.
We can arrest him again.
[KIRILL]
But how--?
I told you. I came to
this place to rescue you.
[gasps]
[DERICK] Hey, Apple! I thought
we called off the air strike!
What's going on?
[APPLE]
We did, but the self-destruct--
is still-- so we'll
have-- Travis--
[DERICK]
Hm? What about Travis? Huh?
Hey, big guy.
I think you'd better put
a pep in your step.
[MAXINE]
All right. They're sending help.
[DEANA] Good. We've gotta
get the hell out of here.
[alarm balres]
Dammit. These guys sure
are a bitch to look after!
[BOTH gasping]
[DERICK]
Not bad, huh? That's my loan.
A hundred thousand Lisvaletta
dollars saving your ass!
You're a good guy, Derick.
And I'll pay you back!
[KAY]
Mm...
Don't you worry.
You've gotta have faith
in them. Look.
He might only give it
the bare minimum, but,
he'll make sure
everything works out.
It's just the man Doug is.
He'll never do what he can't do,
but Doug will always do
what he promises.
Yeah, if Doug swore to you
that he would save the world,
then he'd save it by five
and still clock out on time.
[DERICK] If he really wants
to eradicate poverty
and demolish the class system,
he'll get it done by
the time he retires.
[KAY gasping]
[DERICK] That's the kind of man
Doug Billingham is.
[MILLA] The villain
you captured escapes
and his hideout is
about to self-destruct.
There's no telling how
much time you have left.
Let your guard down now
and you die.
[KIRILL] But, strangely, in this
moment you feel no fear.
Instead, all you notice
is excitement.
Yes, this is exactly the life
I've always dreamed of.
The music's about to
swell triumphantly,
and the theme song
will crossfade in.
The beat will start
driving harder,
and the tempo will pick up.
It seems like the heroes
are gonna make it out
of this one alive.
[KAY gasps]
[KIRILL] No part of it
feels bad in the least.
So, don't think.
Feel so good!
[KIRILL]
This is crazy, Doug!
Do you hear what
you're saying right now?
It's a hell of a lot better than
what happens if we don't do it.
We'd both end up dead.
[KIRILL grunts]
[DOUG] I like that face,
Constable Vrubel.
But save it for when it's
time to do this for real.
[gasps] Huh?
No way in hell
am I using Anthem.
Don't worry. I've got a plan,
and I think it'll work.
[KIRILL] Doug's a little bit of
a liar, to be perfectly frank.
Sure, it's all a big lie.
Deana will get caught,
our decoy,
and that'll throw Cooper
off the scent.
You're right,
that's an awesome plan!
Deana's perfect for it!
[groans]
[KIRILL]
Milla? But, why?
[KIRILL] There's always
something a little shifty
about him, but regardless
he's my hero.
Believe in me, Kirill.
Trust me.
[KIRILL] But doesn't
the one who gets captured
win the title of "hero"? Nope.
That's not how it works.
Doug is the hero, no doubt.
And what does that make me?
The sidekick!
[KIRILL yelps]
[groaning]
Are you okay?
[laughs]
[YURI]
Hey! Kirill!
[helicopter blades whirling]
[KIRILL gasps]
[DEANA]
You can figure it out later!
And kick Travis's ass later,
too, if you want!
[KIRILL] They're here
to rescue us! Come on!
You're almost there, Doug!
Dammit! What are
you waiting for?
[DOUG]
I'm stuck!
[KIRILL gasps]
Doug! No!
Get out of here.
You wanna get caught
in the blast?
Don't try and be a hero!
It isn't a good look for you!
[DOUG]
Constable Vrubel. Listen to me.
What is it now?!
[DOUG]
You clearly don't know me.
Not as well as you think.
I never said I didn't
want to be a hero.
[KIRILL]
Yes, you did!
Something about only
lasting 15 minutes!
Yeah, but, still.
This way I'll always
live on in your heart!
And that's an even
greater hono--
[DOUG gasping]
[DOUG screams]
[KIRILL grunts]
[KIRILL] You really
aren't cut out for it.
Heroes need to be
graceful and dignified.
Then you're disqualified.
Yeah. And that's why
we're detectives.
Guess you're right about that.
The comical type, too.
[COOPER] I'll just have to
take you all with me!
If reinforcements come
down from the colony,
then that will mean
the end of Earth.
[COOPER gasping]
Uh! Zabel?
How exactly did you
manage to get in here?
[ZABEL grunting]
[ZABEL] I came in using
one of those things.
What does "one of
those things" mean?
[COOPER grunts]
[ZABEL] So, you're trying
to be the sole survivor
of the season finale.
Eh, Cooper?
[COOPER]
What? No!
[ZABEL] Don't you think
it's a tall order
for the whole main cast
to make it out alive?
Especially the surprise
villain of the last arc?
[COOPER groaning]
[ZABEL]
Listen to me, Cooper.
Don't think of this as revenge.
I'm still just angry at you
for your terrible habit
of wasting perfectly good food.
[gunshot]
I'm sorry, Derick.
About your bus.
Nah, it's fine.
If you're gonna say
sorry to someone,
then you should
apologize to Milla.
[MILLA]
Hm? For what?
Well, I owe you an apology
for not paying you much, and for
blowing up your workplace.
I don't really care, honestly.
But all I have left on Earth is
the loan, and this little thing.
Uh! You put that
away, right now!
I will throw you off!
It's all gonna
work out just fine.
But now I don't have
any way to pay back
the money I borrowed from you.
[DEANA, KIRILL gasp]
Wait, so, you're his lender?
Oh, don't worry.
Nobody can do everything
perfectly, you know?
Heh.
[KIRILL]
She looks just like her,
but she's still not the
real Yuri, is she?
[APPLE]
No, it's Yuri, all right.
The original, too.
[KIRILL]
Huh?
You had better get Travis
to explain that one.
[KIRILL]
Uh...
[TRAVIS]
I'm truly sorry.
Please. I beg your forgiveness.
Uh. He says this is the
ultimate form of groveling.
Uh...
[NARRATOR] Since Travis's head
is embedded in the ground,
let me explain. I'm sure you
remember a few episodes back
when Travis spilled coffee
down the front of his shirt?
Yep, it just so happened to be
on Yuri's maintenance day.
In a moment of clumsiness,
Travis spilled his
damn bean juice
right onto Yuri's internals!
This caused her to start
acting bizarrely,
which was not a good sign.
Travis decided she just
needed to dry out a bit.
So, he temporarily activated
Yuri's spare body
without consulting Doctor Apple
and stayed up all
night in secret
workin' on the forbidden task
of copying her core data,
tryin' to cover up his clumsy
and unethical deeds!
[YURI]
I'm Yuri!
[TRAVIS exhales]
Then, that awful
explosion happened.
The one we all thought
killed our comrade.
[DEANA]
But that's her, all right.
The real Yuri.
Yuri!
[gasps, laughs]
I'm just glad I take
my coffee black.
If any sugar got in, her
circuits could have shorted out
completely, and that
might have been the end.
[DEANA growls]
Oh. Still got it, Boxer.
That was... a great punch.
Oh, hey, guys!
Travis just told me
that he's buying today!
Nice, huh?
Lucky break.
A lesser man would have
to face real consequences.
Hey, Doug.
[DOUG]
Hm?
[KIRILL] I'm submitting my
resignation to Travis.
I caught a real lucky break
this time around, but
there's a high likelihood
that the people of Nikai
will come after me again.
And the next time, we might not
all make it out unscathed.
[DEANA]
You're such a dweeb!
I'm always amazed at
just how stupid you are.
You could totally hide in plain
sight like you have up till now.
That's right. I'm sure
not gonna tell anyone.
Yeah, and if they do
come back for you,
we'll just have to deal
with them then.
Well, you heard 'em.
And SEVEN-O itself might be
done for the time being, anyway.
Let's not worry
about the future.
[KIRILL] And, so,
that's how the case ended.
They blamed most of it on
Cooper's corruption and treason,
and chalked the rest up to
Esperanza seeking revenge
against him, after he used
and discarded them.
The existence of Nikai
remained a well-kept secret.
As for SEVEN-O's alleged
assault on the military.
We got out of that one partly
because Cooper forced me
into the position
of his adjutant
in order to persuade
me to join him.
Then, when I was made aware of
the full extent of his treason.
I was able to enlist their help
putting an end to
everything he did.
And that's how
it all played out.
Of course, nothing happened
to Morgan or the others.
Milla. I mean, Valery,
still helps out
at Derick's place.
And I'm sure Grandpa Dan would
be happy we're together again.
[KIRILL]
Oh, by the way.
Apparently, Doug has
no idea why Zabel
even decided to help SEVEN-O
in the first place.
Doug said Zabel probably has
some shred of good left in him.
Soon it was election season,
time for the mayoral race.
Right now, the incumbent
is in the lead.
But Dorman is campaigning on a
massive crackdown of drug crime
and seems to be gaining
steadily in the polls.
Wondering why I'm telling
you about any of this?
Well, with Dorman's campaign
appealing to the public,
SEVEN-O wasn't
disbanded after all,
and we're still in operation.
That's right.
Even with Esperanza defeated,
Anthem is still around,
and so are Anthem users.
It could all just
dry up tomorrow,
or maybe it'll never
really go away.
Who knows?
I sure can't predict the future.
So, as long as Anthem
is on Lisvaletta streets...
As long as criminals try
to sell it in our city...
Our work will never
really be done.
Freeze! It's SEVEN-O!
[CRIMINAL 13A]
Uh!
[DOUG] Put your hands on your
head and get down on the ground.
And also.
Tell me what you think has
been the greatest moment
in your life up till now.
Spare no details.
[KIRILL] Yep. This is a story
about ordinary detectives,
working a beat in
a particular city.
Brave men and women who
are willing to risk their lives
in the line of duty
[NARRATOR] Wrong! This is
a story about detectives, sure.
But it's also a story about
a group of heroes.
People who saved the world from
disaster, the true magnitude
of which they themselves didn't
even fully understand.
[SOLDIER 13A] We've lost all
contact with Cooper.
[SOLDIER 13B] I see. Well,
I can't say I'm surprised.
He is the weakest of all
our 144 enhanced soldiers.
[NARRATOR]
That's too many, man!