"E", "E", Extra!
Antony.
[KENSUKE]
"Y", "Y", "Y", "Y", Yokel!
Lao-Tzu.
[YOSHIO]
"U", Un...cool.
[INOUE]
Lepidus.
[KENSUKE]
"S", Shellfish!
[INOUE]
Hammurabi.
[YOSHIO]
"I..."
[KENSUKE] Would you pick
something easier, for once?
[PIPPO hoots]
[NORO]
Crybaby. It's two on one.
And Inoue's giving you a
handicap by only sticking to
BC-era historical figures.
This should have been
a breeze for you two.
Dammit! How long is
the boss on break for?
Even I don't slack
off this much!
--[phone buzzes]
--[YOSHIO gasps]
[NEWSCASTER]
Let me make sure I understand.
You're saying that the Shibuya
Dogenzaka robot incident,
the organ-trading tower scandal,
and the abduction
of police officers
in the underground
discharge channels
were all solved by the same
mysterious cooperant
and not the police?
If that's true, it's incredible.
Do you have any proof of this?
♪
[AKECHI gasps]
Y'know, seeing you dressed like
that really does it for me.
How long are you
planning to ditch work?
[AKECHI inhales]
I guess...
[AKECHI]
...forever, if possible.
♪
[grunts]
[THUG A grunts]
We ain't payin' you jack!
[THUG B]
You've got some balls tryin'
to pull that crap on us!
[grunts]
[THUG A, C gasp]
[THUG C grunts]
Little punk!
What are you do--
[grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES gasps]
[AKECHI sighs]
What am I doing?
The hell's it look like?
I'm stopping you, clowns.
[gasps]
[THUG A shouts]
[grunts]
[THUG C grunts]
[AKECHI gasps]
[AKECHI grunts]
Idiot! He had a gun!
What were you thinking?
[TWENTY-FACES]
Whatever. It's no big deal.
[AKECHI] I can't
believe you kissed him.
Yeah, so. I do it all the time.
[AKECHI]
That's not the point, man!
[TWENTY-FACES gasps]
You're only supposed to do
that with someone you love!
[laughs]
Sorry.
[AKECHI]
Don't laugh!
[TWENTY-FACES]
Sorry.
Thanks for the help, Mister...?
[AKECHI chuckles]
Kogorou. Akechi Kogorou.
[NAKAMURA]
Hey. You in there?
Hello?
[AKECHI groans]
Nao. That actually kinda hurts.
You promised that if I
overlooked your boys'
unlawful actions, all of
the credit for solving these
cases would go to me, right?
You know the answer.
You remind me every day.
Then what the hell
is that crap about?
[AKECHI]
How should I know?
[NAKAMURA] You're the top
story on every single channel.
Twenty-Faces has almost
completely faded
out of the picture.
Well, with a mug this handsome,
they were bound to notice me.
Uh. Still waiting on the
witty-comeback here.
So tell me something.
[AKECHI]
Hm?
[NAKAMURA] What happened
between you and Faces?
[music plays]
[AKECHI]
All right! My song! Let's rock!
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Hey!
[AKECHI]
Relax. You're in for a treat.
[sighs]
[AKECHI] Okay. Listen up, folks.
This is for my beloved Nao.
Put your hands together
and sing along!
[single person claps]
[MEN laugh, chatter]
[TWENTY-FACES] This party
is supposed to be for us.
[AKECHI] Just be happy
we get to drink.
We have a lot
in common, Akechi.
Huh?
You despise boredom.
You're always looking
for the next big thrill.
[AKECHI sighs] Y'know, you don't
have to hang out with me, right?
[TWENTY-FACES]
But you're the only one who can
change my world.
I mean that, Akechi.
I knew it after you rescued me.
Have it your way, then.
[TWENTY-FACES, AKECHI gasps]
Let's see what you can do, kid.
[AKECHI grunts]
[MAN B]
What's wrong?
[AKECHI gasps]
Don't tell me.
This is your first time
handling one of these, huh?
If only that were
the case, sir.
[FEMALE SERVANT A gasps]
Sorry, I'm such a clutz!
I'll bring you a
new one right away.
[KENSUKE] Don't worry about it.
No one was gonna eat it.
You good? No cuts?
I'm... fine.
Then you may go.
[FEMALE SERVANT 7A]
I'm very sorry, sir.
[KENSUKE'S DAD] You know I
don't appreciate that attire.
Dress properly
next time we meet.
[KENSUKE]
Okay.
Sorry, dad.
[KENSUKE]
So, um. What did you need?
Huh?
[KENSUKE]
Akashi called.
He said you wanted to see me.
I figured you needed something.
[KENSUKE'S DAD] I can't ask for
you unless there's business?
[KENSUKE]
Well...
[KENSUKE'S DAD] I hear you run
around, goofing off every day.
[KENSUKE]
I'm not goofing off.
[KENSUKE'S DAD]
I'm not angry, son.
[KENSUKE'S DAD] So long as
you don't cause trouble,
you're free to do as you please.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[KENSUKE'S DAD]
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Another business trip.
If you need anything, just get
ahold of Akashi, as usual.
[KENSUKE]
Hm.
[KENSUKE'S DAD]
Don't forget.
You're the eldest son
of the Hanasaki family.
[KENSUKE]
You know that isn't true.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[KENSUKE]
Woo-hoo!
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[chuckles]
You can't help
being loud, can you?
[KENSUKE] We need to get
you a swimsuit. Stat.
So, that man. You said
he's your father, right?
[KENSUKE]
Huh? Yeah.
Though, we're not
related by blood.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE ]
I was adopted.
The Hanasaki's took in
my older brother and me.
Of course, I'm not actually
related to my brother either.
And he moved out a while ago.
[YOSHIO]
Wow...
A lot can happen in life.
[YOSHIO]
Mm?
Uh. I can actually
hit you with this?
That's awesome!
[chuckles]
[YOSHIO]
Don't you dare.
Whatcha gonna do about it, huh?
[YOSHIO]
Cut it out!
[KENSUKE] Oh, now you've
done it. I'm not holdin' back!
I suppose that's
a friend of his?
[YOSHIO, KENSUKE chattering]
[KENSUKE'S DAD grunts]
Dammit, you're not
playing fair at all!
[laughs]
Let him go!
[SOUSUKE pants]
[gunshot]
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Akechi!
[KOGOROU grunts]
Sou... Sousuke.
Sousuke!
[single person claps]
[NAKAMURA] Jerk. You weren't
even listening, were you?
[AKECHI]
Huh? I did. Loved it.
I especially liked that
cute little voice crack
when you belted out
the chorus of--
Whatever, just tell
me like you promised.
Huh?
You said if I sang, you'd tell
me everything that happened.
Why Twenty-Faces toys with you.
[AKECHI]
Hm. I said that?
Don't try to pull
that crap with me.
It's not cute at all.
Alright... I killed him.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh?
[AKECHI]
My dad... Both of them.
[NAKAMURA]
Uh...
What?
[AKECHI]
Hm?
I'm... not sure where to begin,
to be honest with you.
You killed your dad?
That's just crazy talk!
And what does it have to
do with Twenty-Faces?
Since I killed someone,
I'm evil itself.
That's probably what
he thinks, anyway.
That makes no sense. You, evil?
I mean, come on,
is that masked jerk
putting himself on
a pedestal or what?
[AKECHI]
By his standards, probably.
[NAKAMURA]
So what else?
'Scuse me?
[NAKAMURA]
You know. What happened?
You only sang one song.
That's all you're getting.
If you want any more,
then give me more.
Show me the deepest
part of you.
That's not on the menu.
[AKECHI grunts] Fine. You should
probably get going anyway.
Huh?
You gotta date, right?
Don't wanna be late.
Huh?
[AKECHI] Your nails
are painted, for once.
You just came from
the hair salon.
You didn't eat your favorite
shallots or kimchi because
you're worried about bad breath.
[NAKAMURA]
What?!
[AKECHI] Not to mention... you
shaved all the important parts.
[gasps]
Jerk! What's your deal?
I gave up half my precious day
off to help you feel better.
Thanks for a massive waste
of time. Enjoy being alone.
Wait! One more thing.
Is the guy hotter than me?
[NAKAMURA]
Obviously!
Yeah? Got a picture?
Send it my way!
Come on!
[SOUSUKE whimpers]
[SOUSUKE screams, whimpers]
[SOUSUKE, SOUSUKE'S DAD grunt]
[SOUSUKE groans]
[SOUSUKE'S DAD] I don't
like that look. Quit it.
Wanna leave, Sousuke?
Fine with me. Get the hell out!
What's keeping ya?
[WAITRESS]
Oops. Sorry about that.
Man. That's a waste
of good beer.
Be more careful, miss,
for the suds.
[WAITRESS]
Huh?!
Now the table's all wet. Jeez.
Uh. Could I get a
towel or some...
Would it be okay if I
shook your hand, sir?
Huh?
[phone rings]
Where are you?
We're getting a flood
of job requests!
Huh?
[INOUE sighs] Seriously?
Did you not check your messages?
Oh, no. Sorry, I've been busy.
[sighs]
[INOUE] There's an article
going around online saying
Akechi is the
"mysterious cooperant".
[KENSUKE]
Yikes.
[NORO]
Yikes is an understatement!
We need an adrenaline junkie
if we're gonna tackle
this workload, so get out there!
For real?
[NORO]
For real!
[KENSUKE]
For real?!
[INOUE] Yes! Now, get to
the office. Don't stop--
[pjone beeps]
Finally! C'mon, Kobayashi.
[exhales]
What, right now?
[KENSUKE]
You wanna die, right? Let's go!
[YOSHIO]
Okay, fine.
Can't you move faster?
[YOSHIO]
Oh, shut up.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE]
O-Oh. That's my big brother.
Huh...
[KENSUKE]
Get your clothes on!
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
Oh, wow. Scary.
[AKECHI]
Akechi Kogorou.
That's the detective
that saved my life.
I took his name to honor him.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Detective?
Yeah.
[AKECHI] He rescued me
from my useless dad.
From a life of abuse.
[AKECHI]
As far as I'm concerned,
he's my second father.
[AKECHI] He's the one
who made me who I am.
[KOGOROU]
Don't you worry, Sousuke.
You're nothing like your dad.
You couldn't be.
I know he hurt you a lot,
but now you have the
chance to save others.
[SOUSUKE sighs]
[KOGOROU]
Well? Sound good?
[AKECHI] He filled my
life with adventure,
and the love I never had. But...
But I couldn't protect him.
[gunshot]
[AKECHI]
I was right in front of him,
and I couldn't do a damn thing.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Akechi.
[AKECHI grunts]
I wanted to run away.
Somewhere that no one knew me.
Or even cared for me.
A place as far away from
there as I could get.
[AKECHI exhales]
[AKECHI] But before I did,
I saw my dad one last time.
[SOUSUKE'S DAD]
Hey! The hell're you goin'?
[SOUSUKE'S DAD] You're just
gonna leave your old man
to die like this?
Sousuke. Please.
[SOUSUKE]
That's not my name.
From now on,
I'm Akechi Kogorou.
Alright, fine.
Just remember this.
You chose to leave a
dying man to his fate.
You killed your real father!
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Sousuke!
Sousuke, wait! Don't leave!
Sousuke! Sousuke!
[AKECHI]
Right after I left the country,
he died in his bed.
Both of my fathers are
dead because of me.
♪
[AKECHI]
I've got a good life here.
It provides me with
plenty of thrills.
Makes it easier to
forget the old me.
And, more importantly,
to forget my fathers.
[TWENTY-FACES]
You're my savior, you know that?
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES] To repay you,
I won't let you get bored.
[AKECHI gasps]
I'll be... the greatest
thrill you've ever had.
[AKECHI gasps]
[AKECHI]
Thanks for picking me up.
I hope you can shake off that
bender quickly, Mr. Celebrity.
Ha! I guess we'll
know soon enough.
Everyone except Pippo is out
of the office working cases.
You'll forgive me if
I don't feel reassured.
[TV ACTRESS] If only time
would stop for the two of us.
[TV ACTOR] Funny. I was just
thinking the same thing.
Hey. Question.
[INOUE]
What is it?
[AKECHI]
What kind of... person am I?
Am I supposed to take that
creepy question seriously, boss?
Or is it just another
of your sad jokes?
[AKECHI chuckles] You're more
callous than usual, today.
[gasps]
Don't scare me like that.
[AKECHI] You don't seem
any worse for wear.
[TWENTY-FACES]
I figured it out, Akechi.
[AKECHI gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
I won't kill. Not ever.
That's what I've chosen.
[gasps]
That way, I won't
become evil, like you.
[gasps, grunts]
I'm not a murderer
like the rest of you.
But I'll keep providing
thrills for you.
So many you'll drown in them,
mired in your own darkness.
[AKECHI gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES] I'll fill your
life with so many adventures.
The same way your
namesake did for you.
Things will be so fun for us.
[AKECHI gasps]
My Akechi.
[chuckles]
That's so unfair! How could
you say that to me?
[TV ACTOR]
Quit your yelling.
If you're going to sleep,
then turn that off.
I like listening to it.
Is that so?
[TV ACTOR] Take you money
and get out of my life.
--[static buzzes]
-- Here. Take it and go.
[HARU] We interrupt this program
for a special announcement.
[AKECHI grunts]
[HARU] I represent the
oppressed residents
of the Kokorogaoka
Housing Complex.
I'm sure you'd like to get back
to the show, so I'll be brief.
Just bear with me for a
few minutes of your time.
Now then. The urban
redevelopment program
is a useless waste of resources,
that no one asked for.
We refuse to vacate our homes
for the sake of solving nothing.
We proclaim the entire complex,
from Building A to Building H,
to be named the
"Kokorogaoka Borough".
And, as of this moment, we,
the Borough's residents,
declare independence from
the nation of Japan.
The government
will respect this.
What's this about?
That'll never work!
[KENSUKE gasps]
[HARU]
Thank you for your time.
[YOSHIO]
Hey.
[HARU]
Take care now.
It's Haru.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES] "Paradise in
a Miniature Garden."