[YOSHIO whimpers]
[YOSHIO'S MOM]
Dear....
Listen closely.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[inaudible]
[INOUE]
Kobayashi... Snap out of it.
Kobayashi!
[YOSHIO gasps]
[grunts]
[INOUE]
Let's go.
Dammit.
[INOUE]
Whaddya think?
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[gasps]
[grunts]
[INOUE]
What's wrong?
Talk to me.
[HIDE]
See? We caught up in no time!
[INOUE]
Oh, no.
[INOUE] You're still hanging
with these delinquents?
[HIDE]
Huh? D'you say something?
[KENSUKE]
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's fairly obvious he isn't.
[KENSUKE grunts]
You guys. The hell?
[HIDE] All right,
that's enough of that.
[YOSHIO gasps]
All this tension
isn't helping anybody.
Whatever your beef is,
it can wait 'till this is over.
Now, play nice.
We've got some repressed
memories to track down!
♪
[DETECTIVE B]
This is where it happens.
[MALE DETECTIVE B]
He takes his mask off.
[DETECTIVE A] We know
this man as a detective
by the name of Akechi Kogorou.
We dug into his background,
but there's nothing beyond
the past the seven years.
His name might be an alias.
[BOSS A] So this the
infamous Twenty-Faces.
[MIYANISHI]
That's impossible!
It's another disguise.
He's just trying to fool us.
Calm yourself.
Akechi has gone
mono a mono with
Twenty-Faces countless times.
He can't be two people at once.
So this is obviously a trick!
[DETECTIVE B]
Then, maybe "Twenty-Faces"
is actually a gang name?
[DETECTIVE A] They cause
incidents, then solve them under
a false identity to
take all the credit.
[MIYANISHI] He doesn't
give a damn about credit.
He did what Nakamura
asked and let her take--
[BOSS A]
That's the problem.
[MIYANISHI]
Huh?
[BOSS C]
She leaked investigation
info to a civilian.
I'll deal with Nakamura.
Her incompetence will not
hurt this department again.
[MIYANISHI grunts]
You can't!
[BOSS C]
Find Akechi Kogorou
before the media
gets wind of this.
[MIYANISHI]
One moment!
[BOSS D]
If this gets out, we're done.
[MIYANISHI] At least listen
to what I have to say--
That's enough! Get to work.
[MIYANISHI gasps, grunts]
[YOKOYANAGI] They're trying to
dump everything on Nakamura
to save their own sorry hides.
Damn cowards.
[YOKOYANAGI]
I wouldn't get involved.
[MIYANISHI grunts]
[YOKOYANAGI]
Hm.
[phone buzzes]
[grunts]
[phone rings]
[FEMALE RECORDING] The number
you have dialed is unavailable,
or not in service.
[MIYANISHI]
Damn it!
[MIYANISHI sighs]
I can't get them involved.
Those kids have been
through enough as it is.
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[YOSHIO]
Wait.
[KENSUKE] If you
anything familiar, tell us.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[KENSUKE]
What is it? Need a break?
[YOSHIO gasps]
No.
I was thinking about the
park from your dream,
a red octopus slide.
[INOUE]
A train with green lines.
Even if only remember fragments,
they should all
connect eventually.
Plus, you're still weak.
Don't overdo it.
Wow. Everyone loves you, Koba.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
I want in on this action.
So is there enough
love to go around?
[INOUE] If you want to tag
along, keep your mouth shut.
Hey, why don't you join
the Hooligans, Koba?
You'd have way more
fun than this.
[INOUE grunts]
Stop kidding around.
If you join now, I'll throw
in a super comfy pillow
and Furukawa's Chief position.
[FURUKAWA]
Do I get a say in this?
What's the problem?
The Boy Detective's Club
is done for, right?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[HIDE]
So then...
Shut up, Hide!
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[YOSHIO]
Wait!
[YOSHIO breathes deeply]
[KENSUKE, INOUE]
Kobayashi!
[KENSUKE grunts]
[FURUKAWA]
You okay?
[KENSUKE]
Don't worry. I'm used to it.
[HIDE chuckles] Jeez, Han,
you really never learn, do you?
[YOSHIO]
That way.
[INOUE gasps]
[YOSHIO]
That way, is my...
This man is Twenty-Faces?
Doubtful.
Ask your friends.
They could tell you a
lot better than I could.
[MIYANISHI]
Huh?
[ISUZU]
Say, for instance.
The messenger boy from the
underground waterway.
[chuckles]
[MIYANISHI]
How do you?
--[door clatters]
--[URASHIMA] That's enough.
[MIYANISHI grunts]
[INOUE]
Is this it?
[YOSHIO]
Yeah.
[HIDE] Nice! The dots
are starting to connect!
[KENSUKE] Let's split up
and search the place.
[INOUE]
Hm.
[HIDE]
Sup, Ino? Find something?
[INOUE]
Don't call me weird names.
[HIDE]
Ah... What's this? A diary?
[INOUE] It's a medical record.
Looks like the wife was
terminally ill, and the husband
was treating her here.
[HIDE]
Brutal.
She had Aggressive
Autoimmune disorder.
Despite our advances, we still
don't have a cure for it.
Did this couple
have any children?
It's unlikely. Having a child
would have shortened her
life span that much
more, and besides,
with all the drugs
in her system,
it would have been impossible.
Guess all that reading is
good for something, huh?
[FURUKAWA]
Hm?
[HIDE]
What? D'you find somethin' too?
[FURUKAWA]
Huh? Oh, no.
It's Ayusawa,
the cockroach reviewer.
His photo, address, and
workplace have been exposed.
He's being harassed as we speak.
[FURUKAWA]
Think we took it too far?
[HIDE]
He got what he deserved.
What'd you do?
[HIDE]
Hey, it's one less asshole
posting stupid crap, am I right?
That doesn't justify making
an example out of him!
Maybe if you'd done
this to Lynch Shot,
there'd be fewer creeps
for us to deal with.
The internet would've
crucified 'em, and jerks like
Ayusawa would've thought
twice about posting stuff.
[INOUE gasps]
Shameful!
People can't truly feel regret
until they're put through hell.
It's only after that that
you can try to help them
change for the better.
[INOUE]
Still.
They're scum.
Why take pity on them?
Jeez, Ino, you're more like
Han than you care to admit.
[INOUE grunts]
--[YOSHIO, KENSUKE shout]
--[ALL gasp]
[INOUE]
What's wrong?
Dunno, he just panicked.
It happened when
he saw this door.
[INOUE gasps]
[MIYANISHI] They're trying to
hide something. It's obvious!
[URASHIMA]
I received a call earlier.
Apparently, some of my men
have been loitering about.
[URASHIMA]
Keep your nose of out this.
[MIYANISHI]
Sounds like a threat.
Makes me wonder who called you.
[URASHIMA grunts]
[MIYANISHI] Impressive!
It's as if she was never sick.
She was lucky. Finding a
heart donor when she did.
[MOTHER A] Uh... Nacchan,
time to go home.
[MIYANISHI] Know what I
found when I checked the
Organ Transplant Network?
Leave us alone!
[MIYANISHI] Her surgery records
were nowhere to be seen.
Stop this now or else.
[MIYANISHI] Or else what?
You'll tell on me? To who?
Your daddy,
the Deputy Commissioner?
[MOTHER A gasps]
[MIYANISHI] You know
Doctor Kyoumoto, correct?
[INOUE gasps]
[KENSUKE] You okay?
Need something to drink?
[YOSHIO grunts]
I'm fine.
[HIDE]
If you're suffering this much,
why don't you stop
trying to remember?
[YOSHIO grunts]
You wanna know about
your past that badly?
[INOUE]
Of course he does.
[HIDE]
Hm?
[YOSHIO]
No.
[gasps]
[YOSHIO]
That's not it.
I just want the inside of my
head to stop being such a mess.
[KENSUKE]
Koba.
[YOSHIO] If I fix it, then I
can finally join for real.
[INOUE, KENSUKE gasp]
[HIDE]
You heard him.
[FURUKAWA]
Aw, man!
[HIDE] Dude, we need
to work on your tact.
[FURUKAWA]
You'll wanna see this.
[HIDE]
Huh?
[FURUKAWA] It went
live ten minutes ago.
[AYUSAWA] Alright. If I die,
will that make you happy?
Once Six o'clock hits,
I'll give you what you want.
My blood will be on
your hands. You killed me!
[AYUSAWA] The next time you see
me, it'll be for the main event!
[INOUE]
Pause it!
See that?
[KENSUKE]
He's somewhere near here!
[YOSHIO]
Are we going?
[HIDE] Huh? Here I was expecting
"Let him die" or something.
What?
[HIDE] This kid's not at
all like you said, Han.
[KENSUKE]
Hide!
[FURUKAWA]
Awkward... Now what?
[HIDE]
Eh... Pass.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[HIDE] The guy did it
to himself. Let him die.
So, he deserves this, too?
Uh. Pretty much, yeah.
[HIDE] We're done here.
Let's get going.
[FURUKAWA]
Right.
[HIDE] You guys wanna come?
We're punishing a factory
that's leaking all
sorts of contaminants.
[INOUE]
You must be joking.
[HIDE] Nope! I'm as serious
as a heart attack!
[HIDE]
So, what's it gonna be?
[HIDE] Whatevs. You can
do what you want.
I've got things to see,
and justice to serve.
It's been fun!
[FURUKAWA]
Later.
[YOSHIO]
So, what now?
[INOUE]
You really had to ask?
[KENSUKE]
What else would we do?
[YOSHIO]
Tell me.
We're gonna stop him
from killing himself.
[TV WOMAN ]
The line keeps getting bigger!
And tickets for the Tokyo World
Fair continue to sell out the
moment they're put up!
Opening time is closing in!
[FEMALE RECORDING] Sorry,
this customer is unavailable.
Dammit, Nakamura, pick up
the phone already!
[MIYANISHI]
It's me.
You remember the
organ selling incident?
I think the Deputy
Commissioner was connected
and I have a feeling that's
not the worst of it.
[MIYANISHI grunts] I want to
talk to Kyoumoto somehow.
[MIYANISHI] "Dead following
an issue with an inmate?"
Which inmate?
[MIYANISHI gasps]
Fukiya?
[phone beeps]
[FEMALE RECORDING] Your
message has been recorded.
That connects it...
to Twenty-Faces.
[NORO] Jeez, could you stop
being such a slave driver?
I'm trying to enjoy some
quality cuddle time with Pippo.
Just help us, Noro.
We need to know where he is.
He's somewhere around here.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[INOUE] The shadow angles and
position of the Ferris wheel
narrow down his
possible location.
[NORO] I finished
analyzing the video.
He could be heading to
any of these spots.
[KENSUKE]
That doesn't help!
Try to think like Ayusawa.
He sees his suicide as
a kind of vengeance.
He's sure to pick a place
and method that will draw
the most attention.
[NORO]
Like the top of a skyscraper?
No, he'll want to
cause a commotion
and be a nuisance to people.
[INOUE] With that in mind,
he's most likely at...
The Overpass!
[YOSHIO] Wow and you guys
insist that you're not alike.
[INOUE, KENSUKE grunt]
[MIYANISHI] The special
security you were assigned to?
That was also the
Deputy Commissioner.
He wouldn't stop bragging
about it in his interview.
It's no coincidence
that he suggested it,
one day after the robot rampaged
in the Dogenzaka district.
All the dots are connecting
so perfectly, it's creepy.
Nakamura, please,
just answer your phone!
Let me know you're okay!
[AYUSAWA] If you wanna
blame someone, blame them!
[INOUE gasps]
Found him!
[NORO] A train's schedule
to come through at six!
He's gonna jump right
in front of it!
[AYUSAWA grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Stop him!
You were so eager to
gang up on me!
Did I deserve that?
Was I really that bad?
[AYUSAWA] I have
nothing left to live for!
[AYUSAWA gasps]
[AYUSAWA,YOSHIO'S DAD]
The only choice.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO'S DAD] Is death.
We'll die. End everything.
She called you the
"proof of her life".
What a joke. As if you could
replace her that easily.
[YOSHIO'S DAD]
Without her,
there's no point in
either of us living.
The three of us might
as well die together.
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[gasps]
[YOSHIO'S DAD]
It's all your fault. Why?
[YOSHIO gasps]
Why were you born?
Answer me!
[YOSHIO'S DAD screams]
[screams]
[KENSUKE gasps]
Don't do it!
[NORO gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
I can't forgive what
you did, Kensuke.
[INOUE]
Wanna stay with us?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[KENSUKE, INOUE chuckle]
[YOSHIO exhales, gasps]
My dear boy. Live for me, okay?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO]
It doesn't hurt.
[YOSHIO chuckles]
[HIDE hums]
[FURUKAWA] You were laying it
on a little thick back there.
[HIDE]
Hm?
Getting them to make up.
You didn't have to use cockroach
man to pull it off, you know?
Uh...
What?
[HIDE chuckles]
Uh, right! Caught me.
I was totally just
putting on a show.
Don't tell me you ran away
because it was too
much of a hassle.
[HIDE]
Ahem. No! Course not!
That town wasn't big enough
for two forms of justice.
[FURUKAWA]
Seriously, dude?
[HIDE]
It's true!
[MIYANISHI grunts]
[MIYANISHI gasps]
[MIYANISHI]
What the...?
[INOUE] Wanna head back?
We might find something.
[YOSHIO]
No thanks, I don't need to.
[KENSUKE]
Uh! Why not?
I found what I needed.
Once was more than enough.
--[MIYANISHI grunts]
--[phone beeps]
[phone rings]
[phone buzzes]
[MIYANISHI gasps]
You're okay!
[gasps]
[gunshot]
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Voracious Victim."