[YOSHIO'S MOM gasps]
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
--[door rattles]
--[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO'S DAD]
How do you feel?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO'S MOM grunts]
Fine. Don't worry.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
My head.
[grunts]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[YOSHIO'S MOM coughs]
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[footsteps]
[YOSHIO'S DAD grunts]
[grunts]
[YOSHIO'S DAD gasps]
[YOSHIO gasps]
What is this feeling?
♪
Take care of the rest.
Sir.
[HIDE] 'Bout to have a
grandbaby or something?
Pardon?
[HIDE]
The new room.
Oh, no. There isn't
a baby on the way.
Although. In the sense
that Master Hanasaki has
decided to take in new family,
it may mean the same thing.
[SUMIRE] With the
Stratophere Plane in place,
the New Tokyo World Fair is
almost ready! I'm so excited!
And we won't have to
wait much longer!
Indeed. But, there is
some trouble.
Using the police as guards has
raised some public concern.
Huh? What's wrong
with the police?
They've had several
blunders on their record
over these past few months.
The most recent, of course,
being the attack on the
convicted murderer,
Seiji Fukiya. People are
seeking reputable security,
so that they can enjoy
the event without fear.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[FURUKAWA]
Sorry to interrupt you're rest.
I'm one of the renovators.
We need to check every room as
part of our initial examination
of the property.
[KENSUKE]
Huh, really?
I thought you were just
adding onto the place.
[HIDE] Uh, actually, since the
house is so old, they asked us
to take a look around
and see if any repairs
were needed beforehand.
You know how it goes.
Just a quick look-see and
we'll be outta your hair.
[KENSUKE]
Hello, Hide.
[HIDE chuckles]
Whoa! Damn, Han. Your old
man must be rollin' in it.
Ya think?
If he wasn't filthy rich,
he'd never do this for his son.
[FURUKAWA]
Uh, sorry. "Former" son.
One that might never come
back in the first place.
What's up? Why go
through all this trouble?
No choice. Someone
wouldn't answer my calls.
[KENSUKE]
Uh...
[HIDE] You missed out
on a good one yesterday.
Huh?
[HIDE] There was this guy
smoking near the tracks, right?
Stinkin' up the whole place.
He left the butt on the ground!
So, we gave him a taste
of his own medicine.
All over his house.
That'll do. Let's light'er up!
[HIDE]
Whoa! Not that much!
Now. We're here to
officially invite you
to partake in the next mission.
What?
Well, you see, we found this
awesome hole-in-the-wall
restaurant, and someone's
making problems for it online.
Posting all kinds
of lies about them.
See for yourself.
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
[FURUKAWA] This stuff is more
convincing than you'd think.
[HIDE]
He even hid behind an alias.
We can't let the
coward get away with it.
Eye for an eye is the only way!
Whaddya say, Han? Come with us.
We'll serve justice and
have a blast doing it.
[KENSUKE grunts]
No, Hide. I just can't be
one of your Hooligans, okay?
Sorry.
Wait. You still upset
about the last time?
Thought you'd be over that.
[KENSUKE] Nothing good
happens when I try to help.
I don't know what to do.
[HIDE]
Dude, come on.
Everyone messes up at
some point. It's fine.
Well, s'your loss.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[HIDE] Anyway, if ya get any
interesting missions, hit me up.
I'd be happy to tag along.
[HIDE]
What? Was I being too cold?
No. Not really.
[HIDE]
It's not you, it's just...
There's so many
things I wanna do.
Time's short. So, I gotta move!
[gasps]
[HIDE]
Catch ya later, okay?
See ya.
[HIDE, FURUKAWA grunt]
[FURUKAWA]
You suck!
[FURUKAWA grunts]
[HIDE grunts]
[door clatters]
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[AKASHI]
I'm sorry, sir.
Did some people from the
renovation company come in here?
[KENSUKE]
Yeah.
They said there's
something they want to do.
[AKASHI]
And what would that be?
[KENSUKE grunts]
[phone buzzes]
[KATSUTA] Yes? Sunflowers?
Sure, give me a second.
I'm looking it
up now. Let's see.
Oh, you need seeds? No prob.
Wow, helping out the flower
shop sounds thrilling.
[YAMANE]
I don't get how you do it.
Helping them and studying
for exams would kill me.
[OHTOMO] And you've got
a tennis tournament soon,
if I'm not mistaken.
I like keeping busy.
[OHTOMO] Ah. Has Inoue
dropped by recently?
No.
I guess he's taking care
of Kobayashi. He'll come soon.
Sure, if he doesn't
die of boredom
now that the Boy
Detective's Club broke up.
I give him another week.
So, is there anything we can do?
I hate just waiting around.
You really should
know better, Yamane.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What are you--
[OHTOMO] You shouldn't
worry about other people.
[yelps]
[YAMANE sighs]
Help yourself.
Lighten your own load.
Then you can help
others with their problems.
[INOUE] Kobayashi needs rest.
We'll talk here.
All right.
I'm being transferred.
Really?
Yeah, to Special Security.
[MIYANISHI grunts]
So you were forced
to take responsibility
for what happened to Fukiya.
Don't know what you mean.
It's an honor to act as
security for the World Fair.
I'd have volunteered.
[INOUE]
I'm sorry. This is our fault.
None of that.
[NAKAMURA] By the way, Fukiya
was connected to Twenty-Faces.
[gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
Apparently they made contact
while he was still in prison.
After some "convincing" a few
other convicts confirmed it.
[INOUE]
Then he was behind everything?
[NAKAMURA] That being the case,
it wasn't something we could
handle through
conventional means.
Besides, if I kept
working at the pace
I was in general affairs,
I'd never see my boyfriend.
[NAKAMURA]
I'm done with this.
I just came by to say I
won't be around to clean up
after you brats anymore.
Kay? Go back to being
normal kids. It's for the best.
I swear. I'll find a way to
bring you back, Detective!
[INOUE gasps]
[pants]
[YOSHIO grunts]
Huh?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[NORO]
Hey, what's wrong?
[PIPPO hoots]
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
Ow.
[grunting continues]
[elevator rumbles]
[gasps]
[YOSHIO'S DAD] This is why
I never wanted a child!
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[YOSHIO'S MOM] That child...
is proof... that I was alive.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[NORO]
Hey, Koba! Are you okay?
Say something!
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi!
[gasps]
[YOSHIO gasps]
[grunts]
[NORO]
So, what are you doing here?
[KENSUKE] I was thinking
about what I wanna do.
[NORO]
And?
What came to me was...
...to visit him.
I see.
[KENSUKE] I mean, if I hadn't
dragged him into this...
[elevetor doors hum]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Hey. Where's Boss-man?
[INOUE]
Does it really matter?
[KENSUKE] Have you gotten
in touch with him?
Why even ask me that?
Because I...
[grunts]
Fine, then. I'll go.
[grunts, groans]
Kobayashi!
[gasps]
[INOUE]
What's wrong?
[YOSHIO]
My head is all mixed up.
Your head?
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[screams]
[gasps]
[screaming continues]
[grunts]
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO'S DAD grunts]
[YOSHIO'S DAD gasps]
--[YOSHIO'S DAD grunts]
--[YOSHIO groans]
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[INOUE]
A Ferris wheel.
An amusement park surrounded
by a housing complex.
A park with an octopus slide,
and a train with green lines.
[INOUE]
One matches.
It's most likely Akebono
Amusement Park.
Well, Kobayashi? Make a choice.
What do you want to do?
[NORO grunts]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[INOUE]
Hey! Where are you going?
[YOSHIO]
That amusement park.
[KENSUKE gasps]
You can't!
You still need to rest!
I have to get rid
of this feeling!
[INOUE] What do you
expect to find there?
[gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
Huh?
[KENSUKE grunts]
[grunts]
[NORO]
Hey. Open it.
[INOUE]
Hm?
[NORO]
Open the window! Now!
What for?
Do it! Or I'll bust my way out!
Pippo! Unleash your
"One-Hundred Pecks of Fury!"
[PIPPO hoots]
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Noro?
[PIPPO hoots]
[gasps]
[NORO]
Pippo!
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NORO]
Attack!
--[PIPPO hoots]
--[KENSUKE grunts] Stop it!
[NORO]
Stop!
Pippo...
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Tornado!
[KENSUKE]
Ah! Stop it! Cut it out!
[NORO]
Stop!
Pippo...
--[PIPPO hoots]
--[KENSUKE] Huh?
[NORO]
Um... Thunder Snake!
--[PIPPO hoots]
--[KENSUKE screams]
[NORO]
Stop!
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NORO]
Pippo...
[KENSUKE growls]
Hey!
[NORO] Um, use "Some Kind
of Awesome Move!"
Would you knock it off?
What the hell is this about?
[NORO]
There! Finally!
That's the fire I
was looking for.
Way to go paramecium brain.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[NORO] Good work, Pippo!
Mission complete.
You can come home now!
Huh? Hold on! What gives?
I thought you were
going with Inoue
to keep an eye on Kobayashi!
[NORO] I could. But that's
what you want to do, isn't it?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NORO] I want to relax with
Pippo and a box of chocolates.
So I'm gonna.
[KENSUKE]
But...
[NORO] Why don't you just
go back to being simple?
You kinda suck at being complex.
Sad, really.
[KENSUKE growls]
[NORO]
Home, Pippo! Mama's waiting!
[PIPPO hoots]
[KENSUKE grunts]
[OFFICE WORKERS mutter]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[OFFICE WORKERS chatter]
It's nothing.
[OFFICE WORKERS groan]
[gasps]
[HIDE, FURUKAWA chuckle]
[phone buzzes]
[HIDE]
Hm?
[gasps]
[HIDE]
Hey, Han! What's up?
Yo! Need a lift?
[KENSUKE]
Yep!
Whoa! Let me slow down!
He, he. So, where
are we headed, Han?
The Akebono Amusement Park!
[TWENTY-FACES] It's still
not enough, Akechi.
[alarms blaring]
[POLICEMAN A] He's out!
Find and subdue him!
If he gets outside,
we'll lose him for good!
[POLICEMAN B]
Stop! Get back to your cell!
[MASKED MAN grunts]
Don't think you
can get out of here!
[MASKED MAN]
Outta the way.
[POLICEMAN B gasps]
[POLICEMAN B]
Who are you?
The Fiend with twenty faces,
of course.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Falling CLown."