[TWENTY-FACES]
You don't look well, Hanasaki.
Haven't seen you since we played
on the waterfront.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES] Did you
have a fight with Akechi?
[KENSUKE gasps]
Oh, god. Twenty-Faces!
[grunts, screams]
[TWENTY-FACES] It would be
a simple matter to make you
do as I say, but that
wouldn't be nearly as fun.
[TWENTY-FACES] So, instead,
we're going to play a game,
you and I.
♪
I didn't think you'd
actually come.
You've always stayed
clear of the place.
I'm only here because
you asked for me.
It's still unusual.
By the way, I haven't seen
Kensuke in a couple of days.
[INOUE grunts]
[OHTOMO] I called, but he
never got back to me.
Did something happen to him?
What do you want?
Fine, be that way,
Mr. Frowny-Pants.
Yamane! Any day now!
[YAMANE]
Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
This should be
everything you asked for.
Wire, spare underwater oxygen
cylinders, a lifesaver set,
and the improved adaptive
camouflage umbrella.
S'all yours. I hope they
help you out in the field.
[OHTOMO]
Hm... Ta-da!
The ribs are made
with carbon fiber.
Compared to the previous model,
it's about 47
percent lighter.
[INOUE]
Huh.
At least act impressed!
If it were Kensuke,
he'd be bouncing off
the walls screaming,
"It's so light!
You're a genius, Ohtomo!"
I see.
He's just not that type of guy.
Don't take it personally.
So is this everything?
[OHTOMO]
Hm. There is one more item.
Huh?
[YAMANE yelps]
[OHTOMO]
Sleeping gas.
Just add water to
increase the potency.
[INOUE]
Not bad.
[OHTOMO]
Not bad?
[YOSHIO]
Hey.
[OHTOMO, INOUE]
Huh?
You done yet?
[KENSUKE groans]
[TWENTY-FACES]
You were sleeping so peacefully.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Here.
[coughs]
[KENSUKE gasps]
What?!
[KENSUKE]
Where are we?
[TWENTY-FACES]
And how is it? Tasty, yes?
[KENSUKE]
Don't dodge the question!
[KENSUKE groans]
[TWENTY-FACES] I don't dislike
that look in your eyes.
That said, I think
we can do better.
[TWENTY-FACES] Let's see if we
can improve your expression.
Pay attention.
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Detective Nakamura
is a skillful markswoman.
She subdued him without
hitting his vitals.
[KENSUKE]
Brother.
[TWENTY-FACES]
What is that? Relief?
[KENSUKE gasps]
Even though he asked
to be killed out-right,
instead of having to
suffer through this life?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES] I doubt
he'll ever regain the shine
that you remember
from your youth.
It's all your fault!
You made him this way!
[TWENTY-FACES] I extended my
hand when he needed help.
[TWENTY-FACES] Do you
honestly think that's evil?
[KENSUKE]
Damn right I do!
More than Akechi?
[KENSUKE gasps]
Just... leave me alone!
[TWENTY-FACES]
And what about you?
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[TWENTY-FACES] Do you see
yourself as a valiant hero?
A harbinger of justice?
[gasps]
[bells chime]
This unfortunate soul
didn't make it past ten.
Her favorite things were
soccer and beadery.
And her precious smile
could brighten any room.
She needed new kidneys.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
And she would have gotten them,
if you hadn't interfered.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Remember the facility
full of NEETs?
[bells chime]
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES] Your actions
caused the death of no less than
twenty-two children.
[TWENTY-FACES] And that
number will continue to grow.
But I... Those men... I kept
them from being butchered!
[TWENTY-FACES]
Was that the right thing to do?
What of the children
you didn't save?
[KENSUKE gasps]
Shut up!
[TWENTY-FACES] So, are you
a good person or a bad one?
[KENSUKE]
Stop it! I won't listen!
[TWENTY-FACES]
I understand.
You only perceive the things
that are comfortable.
What a convenient way to live.
Stop it!
[NAKAMURA]
Sorry.
I won't have any work to
throw your way for a bit.
[AKECHI] What? But I'll be
so lonely without my Nao.
[NAKAMURA]
It's your own fault, moron.
I shot a man because you
froze like a first year rookie.
Sorry 'bout that. I owe you one.
[NAKAMURA] Right, just "one".
Anyway, I'm sure a "Master
Detective" will have no problem
finding work without me.
Hey, don't sound so heartbroken.
If it'll help,
I can swing by and massage
those perky sweater balloons.
[phone clicks]
[INOUE]
Ready?
[AKECHI grunts]
Yeah, yeah.
[AKECHI]
This place has seen better days.
[FEMALE CLIENT A]
Please.
I'm counting on all of you.
Don't worry. This'll be
over before you know it.
[TWENTY-FACES] I feel so
sorry for you, poor thing.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[TWENTY-FACES] I know how
much it hurts not to be loved.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[MALE HOST A]
Thank you all for joining us.
We have a special
presentation in store.
Our newest facility, Le Waqua,
is Hanasaki's tenth
large-scale complex.
It's grand opening is
scheduled for tomorrow.
[TWENTY-FACES]
A smile.
You've never seen your
father do that, have you?
[KENSUKE]
Shut up.
[MALE PRESS A] Could you
tell us what sets this complex
apart from the others?
[I would have
to say, "Security".
[MALE PRESS B] Is that
because you plan to guard it
with the latest model
security robots, sir?
[KENSUKE'S DAD]
Yes, that's correct.
[MALE PRESS B] An interesting
choice, considering the Hinomoto
Heavy Industries incident.
Even the police are refraining
from using them. Why aren't you?
These robots are different,
in both manufacturer
and capability.
There can be no comparison.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Well, now. Aren't you curious?
[KENSUKE gasps]
What do you think
he'll have to say
about the Hanasaki's
remaining heir?
[INOUE] The building was
condemned 30 years ago.
But, since then, anyone who's
been tasked with demolishing it
has met with
unfortunate accidents.
And, recently,
there have been reports
of spirits wandering the halls.
So we're bustin' ghosts.
Sounds fun.
Don't be ridiculous.
All we're here to do is find
the cause of the accidents.
Catch the spook, and the
case is in the bag, right?
Simple enough.
Ghosts don't exist.
You might wanna rethink that.
After all, there's an
immortal with us.
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
[INOUE] True, but that
doesn't prove the existance-
[ALL gasp]
They must be angry. How scary!
[INOUE gasps]
[MALE HOST A]
Thank you.
We'll take one more question
before wrapping up.
The gentlemen in the
red necktie, please.
[MALE PRESS C] Do you have
enough confidence in the safety
of the complex to
bring your family?
[MALE HOST A]
I'm sorry, sir.
But questions of
that nature aren't--
Of course, I am. I would
love to bring my son.
But he's so invested in
his curricular activities.
I understand.
No teen wants to hang with
dad on a business trip.
[PRESS laughs]
[KENSUKE grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES] All adults
are liars, in the end.
I mean, it's not as if he
actually cares about you, right?
You're wrong. I'm sure he--
Poor boy. You're like
I was at your age.
I know the pain you feel.
You know nothing.
[TWENTY-FACES] You want
both your father and Akechi
to notice you.
To approve of you.
To praise you.
So badly, it's unbearable.
[TWENTY-FACES] Still think I
don't understand your feelings?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
I'll show you.
[KENSUKE gasps]
You see this?
This is what Akechi's
attention looks like.
[doorbell rings]
Seriously?
You're being overprotective.
[AKECHI]
Mm?
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
If you heat meat to
over 150 degrees,
that's when the
"Maillard reaction" occurs.
Causing the amino acids
and sugars to bond
and bring out the flavor!
In other words, it's chemisty!
Cooking is just a
delicious form of science!
Any jobs?
Not today. I'm taking a
much needed vacay.
Pippo and I have been
working ourselves coo-coo.
I see.
[NORO]
Don't worry.
I'm the healthiest member
of the club, by far.
I work out and
take enzymes daily!
Just look at me!
B-T-Dubs, put in an app
before you come over.
B-T-What?
[NORO grunts] Forget about it.
The food made up for it.
All right.
Uh! You're leaving?
[KATSUTA]
Keep me updated, would you?
[NORO]
Huh?
I mean, I am a former member.
[NORO]
Huh?
His intuition's as sharp
as ever. Annoying.
[sighs]
[AKECHI]
Hey! What's up?
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[AKECHI]
D'you find the ghost yet?
[INOUE]
Huh?
[YOSHIO]
No.
Okay. Let's try a
different approach.
Like what?
[AKECHI] It's probably best if
you handle this one alone.
[YOSHIO]
You're skipping out?
That's what it looks like.
I told you, If we're not around,
you can go nuts in there.
It's a fairly simple concept.
[YOSHIO]
Uh!
[TWENTY-FACES]
This gift. Is from Akechi.
Does it bother you?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
I was killed once.
With this very gun, in fact.
[KENSUKE gasps]
Of course, the death of
a single soul is trivial,
as far as our friend
Akechi is concerned.
[KENSUKE gasps]
I mean, after all,
The "Master Detective"
has killed so many, already.
Heh. Listen to me.
Carrying on as if you know him.
[TWENTY-FACES] If you stay as
you are, he'll abandon you, too.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
He has an insatiable lust
for new thrills
and new pleasures.
Constantly seeking the next toy
that will be the source
of his amusement.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Now that Kobayashi has shown up,
what use does he have for you?
He gives no thought to
toys he's grown bored of.
Akechi's only reason for living
is to chase the next big thrill.
But, to catch his desires,
sacrifices must be made.
Pleasure can only exist
on top of detriment.
[TWENTY-FACES] There is
nothing I won't sacrifice
to be his thrill. To be the
only thing he thinks about.
Tell me, boy. What pleasures
do you want to chase?
What is it that you want to do?
Well?
[gasps]
[AKECHI, INOUE]
Hm?
[WOMAN pants]
[WOMAN grunts]
[YOSHIO]
Hey! Stop running!
[BOTH gasp]
[metallic thud]
The hell?
[WOMAN whimpers]
[AKECHI]
Looks like we caught our spook.
[INOUE]
Please stop joking around.
[AKECHI chuckles]
Yeah, yeah.
[WOMAN gasps]
[AKECHI]
Hey. You okay in there?
[WOMAN gasps]
[AKECHI] Hm. You have to
pay my fee, regardless.
[gasps]
Mom!
Good grief. Did you really
think you'd fool us?
[FEMALE CLIENT A gasps]
The lightbulbs in the
chandelier were custom LEDs
manufactured back in 2010.
Furthermore, the building
in this photograph...
...Opened in 2020.
Aame as the Olympics.
Neither the bulb nor
the building existed
when this hotel was in business.
[INOUE] I'm guessing you
planned to use our firm's recent
celebrity to make
your own headlines?
[AKECHI] Would have been
easier than shelling out cash
to tear the place down.
It's a shame it wasn't a ghost.
Might have been worth something.
No joke.
But, even then, people would
have lost interest eventually.
If you give something
enough attention,
you realize it's not a big deal.
It's how the truth works.
[FEMALE CLIENT A]
Cold bastard.
[AKECHI]
Hm?
Don't you get it?
I'm desperate here!
How am I supposed to live?!
[INOUE sighs]
I'm a detective,
not a life counselor.
Maybe you should find one.
[explosion]
[ALL gasp]
[FEMALE CLIENT A]
How did it?
[AKECHI]
Welp. This case is solved.
Let's get outta here.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Why are you hesitating?
You refuse to say your desires
out loud. Are you scared?
No. I'm not. I'm not!
[INOUE]
What about Kobayashi?
[AKECHI] He'll come
out of there eventually.
Stop it!
I think the kid might be
suited for this kind of work.
[INOUE gasps]
Kobayashi, I mean.
He's a better detective
than most of you.
Even more than me?
[AKECHI]
Sure.
And Hanasaki?
[AKECHI]
He's not a detective.
[gasps]
Akechi.
[AKECHI]
He wasn't cut out for this.
I'm done with his stupidity.
[INOUE]
You don't mean that.
[AKECHI]
Enough. Just forget about him.
[KENSUKE grunts]
Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
♪
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Do you still want to be his toy,
even after he's
tossed you aside?
[gasps]
Unfortunately, The more you
cling to him like a lost lamb,
the more bored he'll become.
You'll never bring him the
excitement he craves, now.
[KENSUKE growls]
I'm not a damn toy!
[TWENTY-FACES] True.
Now you're even less than that.
As far as Akechi's concerned,
you're nothing. You don't exist.
But, there's something
you can do about it.
Just make him into a toy.
[TWENTY-FACES] Imagine how
surprised he would be.
Don't you want to make him pay?
To regret how he's treated you?
I can help you get
your vengeance, Kensuke.
[TWENTY-FACES]
I'll ask once more.
[KENSUKE gasps]
What... do you want
to do at this moment?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Is it to be... a pretend Akechi?
[KENSUKE growls]
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Dammit. I'm... I'm not!
[gunshots]
[KENSUKE]
I'm not.
I'm not anybody's toy!
[gasps]
I'm not.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[KENSUKE]
I'm not like you.
I could never be!
[AKECHI]
Let's go.
[INOUE]
You didn't mean that, did you?
[AKECHI]
Hm?
[INOUE]
About Hanasaki.
[AKECHI]\
Yeah, of course I did.
[sighs]
[AKECHI]
For now.
[gasps]
Whether he wants to
come back to us or not
is completely up to him.
No point waiting for it, right?
[sighs]
[INOUE] So... Still trying
to kill yourself?
[YOSHIO]
Of course I am.
Don't... you like
being a detective?
Inoue.
[YOSHIO]
It's not that.
I... just have a feeling
that this won't last forever.
That's all.
Die before it's over, huh?
♪
[YOSHIO yawns]
[INOUE]
This was here when I came in.
[TWENTY-FACES] Hello, Akechi.
Lovely morning, isn't it?
I've come up with a new
game I think you'll enjoy.
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
As I'm sure you've figured out,
Kensuke Hanasaki is in my care.
A truly interesting
young man, isn't he?
[TWENTY-FACES] Are you
going to come for him, or...
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Do you truly not care
if I keep your discarded
toy for myself?
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
Now what?
[TWENTY-FACES] Try to find me.
Try to capture me, if you dare.
[grunting]
[TWENTY-FACES] Is this
entertaining enough for you,
my dear Akechi?
How I wish I could see
the look on your face.
[KENSUKE pants]
[TWENTY-FACES]
You're quite the actor.
Now the real fun begins.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Cruel Tool."