[GIRL STUDENT A cheers]
You got this!
[grunts]
[GIRL STUDENT B cheers]
Katsuta rocks!
[GIRL STUDENT C]
Win it for me!
Katsuta! Want some tea?
I brought a towel for you!
[GIRLS cheer]
[GIRL STUDENT A] Excuse me.
Um. Take this, if you want.
[GIRL STUDENTS giggle]
[INOUE]
Thank you.
[GIRL STUDENT A gasps]
[INOUE] I'll make
sure Kastuda gets it.
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Uh.
[INOUE]
I know he'll be thankful.
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Uh... But...
Sure.
Hey, you! The light
is green, are you blind?
Please pay attention
while you're driving.
And red hat! Walk or text.
Not both at once!
I can't believe they put
us on patrol duty, too.
Man, I hate this
short-staffed crap.
Well, what can you do?
Security robots were banned
after that last incident.
Robots! Come back to me!
Not so loud, moron!
We're in enough hot water as--
[NAKAMURA gasps]
What the hell?
Something's wrong!
[NAKAMURA]
A patrol car?
[KATSUTA]
Huh?
We got the street cordoned off.
Where's that ambulance?
[NAKAMURA]
Miyanishi!
[MIYANISHI]
Right!
[MIYANISHI grunts]
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Twenty-Faces.
♪
[KENSUKE grunts]
[OHTOMO]
That is a problem.
[KENSUKE]
Right? It rebounds like crazy,
and breaks everything
in the process.
[OHTOMO] It definitely has
some room for improvement.
[KENSUKE] You'll fix it, right?
I really like this thing.
Oh, no. I'm not stopping
at simple maintenance.
Behold!
Whoa! Awesome!
[OHTOMO]
I know.
[yelps]
[KENSUKE gasps]
Sorry, Yamane.
Please stop experimenting
in the club room!
[OHTOMO] Don't be so silly.
Experiments are a requirement.
One could even say that
the purpose of invention
is to experiment.
[YAMANE] But I'm the one
who has to clean up the mess.
[OHTOMO]
You are the assistant.
If all you're gonna do is dump
the crappy odd jobs on me,
I quit.
Fine, But if you quit the
Scientific Experiments club,
the girls will never like you.
Your youth will be
nothing but sorrow.
[YAMANE] Whatever.
Girls don't like me anyway.
If you have time to
make weird comments,
you have time to clean.
[laughs]
You just got told, Ohtomo.
You're part of the
problem too, Kensuke.
Half the messes I deal
with come from you.
I just need a place to nap.
Have a heart dude.
I've got class 'till sundown.
Forgive me if my heart
doesn't bleed.
Some of us have to come to
school at the crack of dawn
every single day.
[OHTOMO]
Cut the guy some slack.
Sure he's only
here once a month,
but because of that, he doesn't
have a single friend here.
So maybe you could
be a little nicer?
But... he's...
The ladies will never like
a guy who loses his cool.
[KENSUKE] Yeah, yeah.
As if you have a life.
And you're lucky
I don't, Kensuke.
If the club wasn't my life,
I wouldn't have time to make
these sweet gadgets for you.
[KENSUKE laughs]
Whoa!
[YAMANE]
Not in the club room!
Any photographs they take
are instantly transferred
back to the source.
Pretty handy, huh?
[KENSUKE]
Yeah! No kidding.
I just need to figure out
a way to keep them airborne.
[KENSUKE] Kobayashi's gonna
flip when he sees 'em.
Kobayashi?
Yeah. A newbie.
Interesting. What can
you tell me about him?
[KENSUKE] Mm... He's kinda like
Yamane, but even more useless.
[OHTOMO] I didn't think
that was possible.
[YAMANE grunts] You jerks
know I can hear you, right?
--[phone ringing]
--[KENSUKE grunts]
Hey, how do I
break this thing?
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[YOSHIO] This "GPS" piece of
junk you were talking about.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[AKECHI]
Hey! Let's go!
[KENSUKE]
Akechi?
He found me. It's your fault,
so do something!
So there's a job, I take it?
Yeah, a big one.
Sweet! Just tell me where
I should go, Boss Man.
Nowhere. Stay right
where you are.
Huh?
[AKECHI] You promised
me you'd go to school
one day out of
the month, remember?
That doesn't change
whenever we get a job.
But, Boss.
Don't call me again until your
classes are done, understand?
Aw, come on! Why did
it have to be today?
[YAMANE, OHTOMO grunt]
I am not picking these
organs up for you again.
[YAMANE grunts]
Give me a break!
[AKECHI] These kids.
Come on, let's go!
[YOSHIO]
Go where, exactly?
Shut up. Just do
what I tell you to.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Now that you've joined
the Boy Detectives Club,
my word is law.
[gasps]
Don't talk down to me!
[NAKAMURA]
That's our job.
We're the adults here,
after all.
I'll make this real
simple for you.
Do your job, or lose
your little hideout.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[NAKAMURA] If you wanna
blame someone, blame him.
He said he wasn't going to
do this job without you.
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[NAKAMURA]
Just get moving
before I kick you
off the premises.
[grunts]
I've never seen a cop
threaten a child before.
Uh, question:
Do you really have a problem
with the kid living up here?
Nope. When it comes to
the Boy Detective's club,
I try to keep my
nose out of things.
That's the agreement Akechi
and I have, at least.
[yawns]
[NAKAMURA] The note
specifically said to watch it
with you present.
So, I haven't seen it yet.
[NORO] Maybe it'll self-destruct
after you watch it,
like in those cheesy
old spy movies.
[NAKAMURA]
Who knows?
Senior Officer Kanda, the other
passenger, is still missing.
And Officer Imaizumi
passed out from shock,
so he didn't see
the culprit's face.
[KANDA] It's time for the
game to begin, Akechi.
The rules could
not be simpler.
You have until
nine P.M. tonight.
I hope you didn't take
too long to watch this.
If you can rescue this foolish
police officer by then,
you will win the game. Fail to
do so, and victory is mine.
Believe me, you don't
want that to happen.
[KANDA gasps]
If I win, our officer friend
just might be promoted two
ranks before the night is done.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[NORO] It means he'll be
killed in the line of duty.
Uh. You didn't have
to explain it.
Something's off.
This isn't like Faces.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but wasn't his motto that
he never killed people?
[TWENTY-FACES]
Yes, exactly right.
That's my policy, Akechi.
Good memory.
How's he talking to us?
[AKECHI] Hm. The creep predicted
how I would react, huh?
[TWENTY FACES] Killing someone
would violate that policy,
and I have no
intention of doing so.
However, if the good
policeman were to die
in a tragic accident, well,
that's another story.
Helping others also
violates my policy,
and I'm a stickler when
it comes to my moral code.
A psychopath with standards.
This must be such
a hassle for you.
[TWENTY FACES] Not nearly as
much as being a detective.
You made your point
the first time, Faces,
now you're just
being a show off.
We'll be waiting, Akechi.
Don't be late.
[ALL gasp]
[NORO]
Holy crap, it really blew up!
[NAKAMURA shouts]
You've got to be kidding me!
Please calm down, Inspector.
I'm gonna beat this freak,
even if it's the
last thing I do.
[AKECHI] Guess you don't
need my help, then.
Boss!
I'm just not feeling
this one, is all.
I don't really care
about your guy, anyway.
[NAKAMURA]
Hold on.
[AKECHI] I have a right
to choose the jobs I take.
I won't believe you'd
just abandon a hostage.
I second that. Please, sir!
[sighs] Fine. If he
agrees to it, I will too.
[YOSHIO]
Hm? No way, I hate the police.
You just had to
threaten him, didn't you?
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Me?
Come on, please, kid?
You'd be helping to
save someone's life.
And why would I want to do that?
[MIYANISHI grunts]
Let's say he survives.
If I helped, will I get
anything out of it?
[INOUE]
That's enough!
Does human life mean
nothing to you?
[YOSHIO]
Not really.
[INOUE gasps]
[YOSHIO] Last time I checked,
humans were everywhere.
If one dies, it's not gonna
change anything.
You can't be serious!
Oh, shut up! You asked,
I answered. End of story.
You little brat!
[AKECHI]
Nao, I'll do it.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh?
[AKECHI] Seeing him this
pissed off is new to me.
It's kinda interesting.
[NORO]
True!
[INOUE] Please don't
treat this like a joke.
This is not like
what we discussed.
Enough. It's decided,
and that's it.
But, I'll make you a deal.
If you and Inoue make nice
and solve this case together,
I'll buy you hamburgers.
As many as you can eat.
You really think he'll
go for the cheap stuff?
[YOSHIO gulps]
With cheese on 'em?
[MIYANISHI]
Does that answer your question?
Good. Now play nice.
Only because you
ordered me, boss.
[YOSHIO exhales]
Fine.
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
Katsuta.
Hey. Make sure he gets these.
[chuckels] Flowers for a guy?
And you even put them in a pot.
[KATSUTA]
That's right.
Uh!
[KATSUTA]
I couldn't...
I just didn't want to
cut them, alright?
Gotcha.
Wanna stay? I can
wake him, if you'd like.
Maybe next time.
He knew you were faking.
Why keep it up?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KENSUKE]
Three more hours.
[NAKAMURA]
Well? Figure anything out?
[NORO] The Pippo camera
is shot all to hell.
Which... means... no.
[MIYANISHI] What now?
Old fashioned footwork?
Searching blindly
won't do us any good.
[NORO]
What do you think, Inoue?
[YOSHIO]
He's asleep.
Am not! I'm trying
to concentrate!
Think you can remember anything?
[INOUE] Does Officer Kanda
have problems with his eyes?
As far as I know, he's got near
perfect sight. What's up?
His blinking looked unnatural.
Was it intentional?
Maybe... Morse code?
New.. Out...Er... Dis...
charge... Chan...nel. Stop.
The waterfront!
You heard him.
Get backup out there!
But, surely he would
have moved him by now.
He's there. Once Faces
makes a rule he follows it,
no "ifs", "ands", or "buts".
--[NAKAMURA] Let's go!
--[MIYANISHI] Right!
[INOUE]
I'll arrange for a car.
So how do you know he's right?
He may have an attitude problem,
But his mind is sharp.
[TWENTY FACES]
Hm. Time to begin.
How's it going?
He's annoying me.
[KENSUKE]
Who? Inoue?
I'd rather be stuck
with you than with him.
[KENSUKE]
Aw, how sweet.
This place is gigantic.
We're not gonna find this guy.
[INOUE]
We're not the only ones looking.
[YOSHIO]
Mm?
[KENSUKE] Guess it's just
a matter of time, then.
Aren't you still in class now?
Boss told you not to
call till you're done.
I still don't get it.
If the police are on the case,
then why do they need the
help of a bunch of kids?
You're right, something is off.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Kanda's message to us
was so easily overlooked.
It's hard to believe Faces would
make that kind of mistake.
And?
[KENSUKE] Hm. Sounds like
there's more to it than that.
Wha..?
We must be too far underground.
[INOUE]
This way.
Hey!
[YOSHIO]
That's just a dead end.
[INOUE]
Huh?
I've been using this
route for a long time.
[exhales]
This path of yours.
It's isn't on the map.
The map must
be wrong, then.
No, I made sure to print
out the latest edition.
[INOUE gasps]
Be quiet!
What for?
Just Do it!
[INOUE gasps]
[YOSHIO]
Hey, what are we hiding for?
[INOUE grunts] Some people are
heading straight towards us.
If we follow them we might find
where Twenty-Faces is holed up.
Well, then why
didn't you say so?
[MASKED MAN A] No sign
of anyone on this side.
Is the plan still on?
Right. Heading that way now.
Let's move.
[MASKED MAN B]
Yeah, yeah.
[MASKED MAN A, B gasp]
[MASKED MAN A]
What's that?
[INOUE]
Damn!
[MASKED MAN A, B gasp]
[MASKED MAN B grunts]
[MASKED MAN A grunts]
Huh!
[INOUE] Don't just stand there!
Go get help, you idiot!
[grunts]
[INOUE grunts]
[INOUE]
What are you doing? Run!
Hurry up!
[KATSUTA]
Hold on!
There might be another
suspect here! Stop!
We should wait for Akechi!
Even if it means more victims?
[KATSUTA]
Yes!
[INOUE]
Even if the culprit gets away?
[KATSUTA grunts]
--[gunshot]
--[VICTIM screams]
Inoue!
[MASKED MAN B] Dammit!
I'll feel that for a week!
Huh? Hey, kid.
Aren't you gonna help him?
What's the deal?
[YOSHIO]
Why should I?
[MASKED MAN B gasps]
That's cold. Damn.
But, your pal was right,
you should leave.
You won't get a second chance.
[gasps]
You're not running?
There's no reason to run.
[MASKED MAN B]
You'll die!
If only that were true.
[doors slam]
[KENSUKE] I'm not paranoid.
Those two are in danger!
[NORO]
Quit freaking out.
They're probably just out
of the signal's reach.
Sure. But, if something
is wrong, we'd never know!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't you still have
classes for a little while?
You skipping out?
[KENSUKE]
Why, you gonna tattle?
[NORO]
Of course, I am.
I'm not getting
dragged into your B.S.
Jeez. That's happened
a lot today.
[KENSUKE]
Katsuta!
Done with tennis
practice already?
Yeah.
[KENSUKE] You're still in
the gardening club, too?
Yeah.
[KENSUKE]
And judo?
Yeah.
Y'know, if you have
all that time,
you could've stayed in
the Boy Detectives' Club.
Ever since you quit, the rest
of us have had it pretty rough.
I'm an idiot. Noro's a homebody,
and Kobayashi, the new kid,
is next to worthless.
Aw, come on, man. We could
really use your help!
Sorry, I don't have
time to chat.
[KENSUKE] Uh! Nah, it's cool,
I should get going anyway.
I hope you mean back to class.
Damn. Now you're gonna ride
me about that, too, huh?
Listen to him.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Akechi knows his stuff.
Try putting stock in it.
[KENSUKE gasps]
'Kay.
Good talkin' with ya.
[INOUE gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
[gasps]
[INOUE]
I'm sorry.
You don't need to ask
for my forgiveness.
Just your own.
[INOUE grunts]
[YOSHIO grunts]
It's about time you woke up.
What happened while I was out?
[YOSHIO] The two goons
that kicked your ass
locked us in here.
Why didn't you run?
You keep ordering me around.
I hate it.
Dear God. You are
just impossible!
We've been down here forever!
The others might--
[YOSHIO] Be quiet. I just
have to break us out.
What the...?
Nice plan you got there.
[YOSHIO scoffs]
[YOSHIO grunting, panting]
[INOUE]
Why did you stop?
I need to rest a bit.
There's no time! Break it down!
Why don't you do it yourself?
What?
[YOSHIO]
That's right, you can't.
I'm the only useful
one between us.
You scum.
What are you so mad about?
It's the truth, isn't it?
The truth? The only truth here
is that you're not worthy
of being a Boy Detective!
--[water crashes]
--[gasps]
Still on break,
or are you through now?
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
I just don't see the appeal.
No kidding.
[AKECHI] Nurses should
have skirts, not pants.
[MIYANISHI]
You said it.
[NAKAMURA]
Heads out of the gutter!
[MIYANISHI]
Sorry.
So, d'you get
permission to see him?
[NAKAMURA]
Of course I did.
Wait. He's still injured.
Shouldn't we give
him time to rest?
No way. Not while a hostage's
life hangs in the balance.
That's right.
Keep your mouth shut
and follow my lead.
[NAKAMURA]
Excuse us.
We need your help
finding Ka--
[gasps]
Hey! What are you doing?
Now, then.
I'm Akechi Kogorou, head of
the Akechi Investigation Firm.
[AKECHI] Tell me. What's your
role in this, exactly?
[IMAIZUMI gasps] Sorry, I'm not
sure what you mea-
[grunts]]
[AKECHI] For someone who just
survived a head-on collision,
you barely have
a scratch on you.
You must have the devil's luck.
Or you knew it was coming,
and shielded your face.
Also, the message you
were holding in your mouth.
You were supposed to be out
cold, yet somehow managed to
keep it firmly between
those pearly whites.
I don't buy it.
You're working for Twenty-Faces.
[IMAIZUMI chuckles]
That's right, and he told me
to deliver another message,
just for you.
"Hello, Akechi the Murderer."
[IMAIZUMI chuckles]
Ah...
[gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Why is time so slow?
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Spider's Thread."