[INOUE grunts]
[grunts]
[pants]
[INOUE]
Don't get so irritated.
[KATSUTA] You're still
going to keep it up?
[INOUE]
I could go a few more rounds.
[KATSUTA]
No, I mean Akechi's thing.
The tournament's coming up,
so I wondered.
[INOUE]
Here.
[KATSUTA]
Mm?
I'm not giving anything up yet.
Not tennis, investigating,
or anything else.
[KATSUTA grunts]
Greedy bastard.
[grunts]
[INOUE]
So, what about you?
[KATSUTA]
Huh?
[INOUE] You're sticking with
the detective's club, right?
Actually...
[IMAIZUMI grunts]
[AKECHI] Run your mouth again
and you'll regret it.
Tell me everything you
know about his plan.
And be quick about it.
[IMAIZUMI giggles]
He's sure got you angry.
You must really be tired
of losing to him. Heh.
[groans]
[AKECHI] Told you you'd
regret it. Now spit it out.
[KATSUTA]
I... I can't be like Akechi.
What does that mean?
[INOUE grunts]
[INOUE coughs]
Loser.
Shut up!
[school bells ringing]
--[door slams]
[GIRL A] Huh?
[KENSUKE]
Freedom!
[gasps]
Here I come!
♪
[NAKAMURA]
Dammit, Akechi! Let us in!
[NAKAMURA grunting]
[IMAIZUMI]
It's funny.
He got the idea for this game
after seeing you again.
That so?
[IMAIZUMI]
He was so happy.
That facility was a
veritable treasure trove.
You're a fool if you think
he left without getting
something for his trouble.
[AKECHI]
Hm?
[IMAIZUMI] Do you know what
guards the New Outer Underground
Discharge Channel
during peacetime?
Take a guess.
[AKECHI] He has all the
data on those channels.
No wonder he set
the stage there.
[IMAIZUMI] The security and
drainage control systems
work per his will. You lost
the game before it started.
[AKECHI] So. What's our
dear "sewage king"
plan to steal next?
[IMAIZUMI] Probably the
public's trust in the police,
if I had to guess.
[AKECHI]
Trust?
[IMAIZUMI] You're clueless.
How many dozens,
or even hundreds of police are
in that labyrinth as we speak?
[gasps]
[IMAIZUMI]
That's all your getting.
[door clatters]
You have some nerve, Akechi!
[AKECHI]
Time to go.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh?
[AKECHI] It turns out...
there's more than one hostage.
[KENSUKE]
Wait, what? You sure?
[AKECHI]
Think about it.
What happens if those channels
are filled with water right now?
[KENSUKE gasps] But I thought
Twenty-Faces didn't kill people.
[AKECHI]
Hm. The only absolute
is that there are
no absolutes, kid.
[KENSUKE]
How's Inoue?
[AKECHI] Someone's
jamming communications.
We can't get in touch with him
or any of the
officers down there.
[KENSUKE]
Told you, Noro!
[NORO]
Bite me, junkie.
How does that old saying go?
"Even Homer sometimes nods."
Nobody's perfect.
[AKECHI]
Ain't that the truth.
Have you broken through
the comm jam yet?
I should be able to crack
it in... 20 minutes.
[KENSUKE] So what am I
supposed to do, Chief?
Rescue the hostages?
[AKECHI] We've got 52
minutes left. Hop to it.
[KENSUKE]
If I had skipped class,
this would be over by now!
[AKECHI]
Stop talking. Move!
[sighs]
[KENSUKE]
Yeah, yeah.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Katsuta!
Katsuta, Katsuta, Katsuta!
[KENSUKE laughs]
Forget it.
I haven't said anything yet.
Don't care.
[KENSUKE] We've got
real trouble this time!
[KATSUTA]
I'm working.
[KENSUKE] Come on, man!
Inoue's in danger!
[gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Just for tonight, okay? Please?
[KENSUKE groans]
[KATSUTA sighs]
[KATSUTA]
Get on.
[KENSUKE]
You mean... on top?
Is that the best
your power can do?
[pants]
Who do you think
I'm doing this for?!
[INOUE]
Just go.
[gasps]
Huh?
You can get out of here on
your own. Just follow the water.
Go through there.
Find the others.
Tell them the map is a fake.
They need to cut the
investigation short
and evacuate as
soon as possible.
That means now! Hurry!
And you?
[INOUE] I'll climb this and
try to get out through there.
[INOUE] My chances are slim.
Forget that and focus on--
Yeah. I got it.
[INOUE gasps]
He didn't ask about my leg.
That's Refreshing.
[INOUE grunts]
[gasps]
--[gunshot]
--[BOTH gasp]
Inoue!
[KATSUTA grunts]
Don't go!
I won't just give up!
[gasps]
He wasn't any help
after all. Just my luck.
[gasps]
[VICTIM gasps]
Mercy!
[CRIMINAL]
After you ruined everything?
You gotta be punished for it!
Stop!
[CRIMINAL grunts]
Bastard!
[shouts]
[CRIMINAL grunts]
I don't want to have
to hurt you, too!
[VICTIM gasps]
[INOUE]
Will you come quietly?
[VICTIM sighs]
[INOUE gasps]
[KATSUTA]
Behind you!
[INOUE, VICTIM gasp]
[CRIMINAL]
Hm!
[VICTIM gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
Inoue!
[gasps]
[VICTIM, INOUE gasp]
[INOUE]
Look out!
[gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
[grunts]
[NURSE A] He's worked so hard
at his rehab. Poor thing.
[NURSE B]
It's odd that he can't stand up.
His left leg wasn't injured.
[NURSE A] I guess the
psychological trauma
was just that severe.
[NURSE B]
You mean it's all in his head?
[INOUE]
Sorry for the trouble.
I'm gonna focus on being a
leader to the rest of you.
[INOUE]
What's the job? Well?
There is no job.
That't not why I'm here.
'Scuse me?
[KATSUTA]
What about rehab?
[INOUE grunts]
[KATSUTA] I thought you
weren't gonna give up.
I'm sorry. This is
all I can do now.
[KATSUTA] I can't.
I can't see you like this.
[grunts]
Then leave!
[gasps]
[POLICEMAN A]
Time's almost up.
[POLICEMAN B]
Let's try this one.
[BOTH gasp]
--Hey, let us out!
--What the hell?
[KENSUKE]
Hey! Get out!
Don't go any further,
you'll die!
Be quiet!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Do you want Twenty-Faces to
know we're on to his plans?
[KENSUKE] No, but we're
almost out of time.
We need to avoid
unnecessary fighting.
[KENSUKE]
Fine. What next?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[KATSUTA grunts]
[YOSHIO inhales]
Hell of an entrance, Kobayashi.
[KATSUTA]
What is going on?
[KENSUKE]
I'll explain later.
[pants]
[KENSUKE]
What?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
Damn.
[POLICEMEN chatter]
[KENSUKE]
Boss!
About time.
Is this really everyone?
[MIYANISHI]
No. It's only about half.
Okay.
Then we should at least get
everyone that's here outside.
[AKECHI]
That's what I said, but...
[gasps]
[NAKAMURA] They won't leave
their comrades to die.
They want to keep searching.
The police have a sense
of pride, too, you know?
Yeah. But...
[AKECHI]
Don't panic.
If we beat Twenty-Faces,
we can save every one of them.
I guess. Our only choice is to
keep searching the long way.
[KENSUKE]
Oh, right.
Inoue said the map of
the channels was fake.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE] He said without a good
map, there's no way to search.
[POLICEMAN E]
Great, perfect.
[POLICEMAN C]
Looks like we'll have to go back
and get the
originals then.
[POLICEMAN D]
We don't have time!
[KENSUKE] Don't worry about it!
Leave everything to me.
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki.
Huh?
Why isn't Inoue here with you?
[pants]
[INOUE] I should have
apologized much sooner.
[INOUE grunts]
[gasps]
Inoue!
You're... here.
[KATSUTA, INOUE grunt]
[gasps]
[KENSUKE] Test, test.
You there, Katsuta?
[INOUE]
Huh?
[KATSUTA]
Noro's as fast as ever, huh.
[KENSUKE] For sure.
Did you get to Inoue in time?
[KATSUTA]
Yeah.
Hey, what's going on?
[KATSUTA grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Now that's outta the way...
...time to kick out
the party favors.
Noro!
[NORO]
Here we go!
[KENSUKE]
Fly my pretties!
The police should have
the data momentarily.
Put... me down.
The exit's just up ahead.
Don't care! Stop!
Hanasaki, where are you?
[KENSUKE]
Uh. It says... grid E-12.
Okay, then head
straight for E-13.
[KENSUKE]
Wha...? But...
We don't have time to wait for
the map to be updated. Go! Now!
[AKECHI grunts] Inoue can
be a real slave driver
when he wants to.
Nao, we're going on ahead.
[MIYANISHI gasps]
[NAKAMURA] Just what
are you planning to do?!
We've got a problem.
[NAKAMURA]
Now what?
[MIYANISHI] There's a
swarm of press outside.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh?
[MIYANISHI] Apparently,
Twenty-Faces sent a message
to every media
outlet in the city.
That cocky freak is trying to
make a laughing stock out of us.
[INOUE]
Turn right next.
[KATSUTA] How do you know
that's the right way?
[INOUE] Because I
memorized the fake map.
By looking at the
overwritten locations,
I can narrow down what
path they should take.
[KENSUKE]
What do you think, Boss?
Is Twenty-Faces really trying
to drown all these people?
Hard to say.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Hey! Kobayashi!
[AKECHI]
He must be wiped out.
[KENSUKE]
Yeah.
Pretty ironic, don't you think?
For someone who wants to die,
he pushed himself like
someone desperate to live.
[INOUE]
Focus on the task at hand.
Keep going and you should
reach an open space.
[KENSUKE]
Okay.
It still feels
pretty cramped here.
[INOUE]
Not yet. In another 80 meters.
[gasps]
Five minutes left in the game.
I thought you would
be here sooner, Akechi.
[AKECHI] Yeah, well it
doesn't matter. A win's a win.
[TWENTY-FACES]
True.
[KENSUKE] Hurry and return
the hostage, you creep!
[TWENTY-FACES] Which hostage?
You'll have to be more specific.
Huh?
[INOUE]
He means the other officers
investigating the tunnels.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Is that Inoue's voice I hear?
[INOUE] He's locked them
in various places
throughout the channel.
There are some sealed locations
that look out of place.
That's probably where they are.
Very good, but why do you think
I would use such a tactic?
[INOUE]
To lower trust in the police.
You released water into the
channel to seal them in.
Hey, Inoue. When I want you
to do my job, I'll tell you.
Too bad your plan
didn't work, Faces!
Oh, is that so? Were you
not paying attention?
I said you would win the game
only if you took
the hostage back.
[KANDA grunts]
[gasps]
We still have plenty of time
for a quick game of tag!
[KENSUKE]
Oh! That's so cheap!
[AKECHI]
Hold on!
[INOUE]
Three minutes to go!
That's more than enough.
[AKECHI]
Don't panic. Focus.
Right!
[grunts]
[gasps]
It's that kid!
[shouts]
[MASKED MEN grunt]
[gasps]
[grunts]
Hm?
Kobayashi!
[YOSHIO gasps]
[gasps]
Hanasaki!
On it!
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Huh?
[KENSUKE, KANDA grunt]
It's over! We got him!
[INOUE sighs]
As you just heard,
our investigator safely
rescued the hostage.
[KENSUKE]
You really have lost this time.
No fair, Akechi.
Huh?
[TWENTY-FACES] You kept
some cards up your sleeve.
I wasn't aware that you had
such an interesting toy.
Kobayashi isn't a play thing!
[YOSHIO, KENSUKE]
Huh?
Alright? Remember that!
And that goes for every
other member of the
Boy Detectives Club, you freak.
They aren't toys
for your amusement!
I've never seen you this
heated up before, Akechi.
And I don't like it one bit.
Stop!
Well. Guess I should free
the rest of the hostages.
Nao better throw in a bonus
for all the extra work.
He cracks me up.
[POLICEMEN shouting]
[PRESS chattering]
[KATSUTA] That scrawny kid.
He asked me to get you out.
[INOUE]
Kobayashi?
[KATSUTA] He said he
couldn't help you himself.
[INOUE sighs]
I'm sorry.
[KATSUTA]
For what?
[INOUE]
Don't make me say it.
It's hard enough having
you carry me like this.
[KATSUTA] I'm not cut
out to be a detective.
I know that now.
[INOUE]
Katsuta.
[KATSUTA] I can't accept
you like Akechi does.
[INOUE gasps]
[KATSUTA] I think I'll
be a police officer.
[INOUE gasps]
If you're gonna be
like Akechi someday,
then I'm gonna be your Nakamura.
I've made up my mind,
so deal with it.
[INOUE gasps]
[NAKAMURA] They're searching the
perimeter of the hospital, but--
[AKECHI breathes deeply]
Yeah, I doubt they'll
find any trace of him.
[INOUE grunts]
You should take it
slow for a while.
[INOUE]
Wish I could.
But I don't have a choice.
I can't let Kobayashi
call me useless again.
[chuckles]
So, uh. Thanks, by the way.
Is it your first time
eating these, too?
No! I mean Inoue.
Huh?
You pushed yourself
till you passed out
just to save his life, remember?
If he died, I wouldn't
get any of these.
Ah. Now I get it.
[YOSHIO]
Don't eat another!
What?! You've got a
mountain of 'em!
[YOSHIO]
Akechi got all these for me.
[KENSUKE grunts]
You're so stingy!
[YOSHIO]
Shut up!
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Holiday Stalker."