[HIDE hums]
[HIDE] ♪Won't you please
give one to me?♪
[humming continues]
♪If you do, I'll
treat it true.♪
[humming continues]
[HIDE] ♪I don't need a
sword to slay the demon.♪
♪Your kiss will keep me going
strong hm-hm-hm-hm."
[MALE REPORTER] This just in.
Police are investigating reports
of gunfire after a truck was
overturned in Shibuya.
No leads have been
found at this time.
We'll update as more
info becomes available.
[FUKIYA]
Bird.
[YOSHIO]
Sky.
[INOUE sighs]
[FUKIYA]
Female.
[YOSHIO]
Not male.
Tomorrow.
[YOSHIO]
Don't care.
[FUKIYA]
Life.
Don't need it.
[FUKIYA]
Embrace.
Em... what?
Embrace. It's another
word for hug.
[YOSHIO] Like I'd
know anything about--
[gasps]
[YOSHIO'S MOM pants]
[YOSHIO gasps]
♪
Got more company.
Indeed.
[NORO]
What's up?
Send a helicopter
to the rooftop!
Shouldn't we get your
bosses in on this?
The plan's been shot to hell.
[NAKAMURA]
You kidding?
We'd be dead by the time they
finished pointing fingers.
Yeah, you got a point.
How long until you
can get one here?
[NORO] I'd say about 15 minutes,
give or take a few.
[NAKAMURA]
Might as well be an eternity.
[NORO] I picked the one
that should make it easiest
to get to the courthouse.
[NORO] At least tell your
bosses to beef up security.
[NAKAMURA]
Hm?
[NORO]
I broke through their firewall
like it was tissue paper.
Go ahead of us, Kobayashi.
Why?
You're the only one who
can keep the rooftop clear
for the helicopter.
Huh?
He can't! We're in the
middle of our game,
and he promised he
would play with me!
[NAKAMURA]
Hey! This is life or death!
[FUKIYA] If you insist
on ignoring me...
...then I won't take
another step.
[INOUE grunts]
Tell me.
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[FUKIYA] What came to your
mind after that last word?
Don't remember.
[FUKIYA] Really? Or could
it be that you're afraid?
Afraid of your past.
'Course not.
[FUKIYA]
Your eyes say otherwise.
They've contracted.
That's a sign of adrenaline.
[YOSHIO]
What?
And a sudden increase in vocal
pitch occurs as a result of
elevated airway pressure
flowing past the Adam's apple.
[YOSHIO]
You're not making sense.
[FUKIYA laughs]
Why don't you explain it?
Motor perception. It's basically
a barometer for lying.
Huh? But, I'm not lying.
I swear I'm not!
--[door clatters]
--[gasps]
[VIGILANTE A]
This floor's clear!
[VIGILANTE B]
Split up and find them!
[NAKAMURA] We don't have
time to play Psychiatrist.
[FUKIYA]
How annoying.
Well, I might be
able to remember.
[FUKIYA]
Oh?
But you have to keep moving.
My boy, you continue to
impress and surprise me.
Very well. Let's go to
the depths of your mind.
I don't like when you talk
like that. Makes me feel slimy.
[FUKIYA chuckles]
Rifle.
Noisy.
[FUKIYA]
Detective.
[YOSHIO]
A way to die.
Akechi Kogorou.
[YOSHIO]
Reeks of booze.
Crimson.
Wha--
[grunts]
A wall.
[FUKIYA]
Hm? A wall?
Crashed into.
[FUKIYA]
Tears.
Crashed into.
[FUKIYA]
Tears.
Disgusting.
Kensuke Hanasaki.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO]
A freaking idiot.
[MALE REPORTER] If you're just
tuning in, we're continuing to
cover the armed
transport of Seiji Fukiya,
the killer of a Yoyogi Girls'
Middle School student.
[HIDE]
Here. You'll need this.
[KENSUKE]
What?
You should see your face, man.
Don't get too excited, the real
surprise is yet to come.
[KENSUKE]
This is.
I know, right?
And after all the hard work we
put into decorating the place.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
It's a cryin' shame.
We were gonna treat
him to his last meal.
[KENSUKE gasps]
But now that his escorts
have gotten in the way,
we'll have to attack head-on if
we wanna bring him to justice.
Start making sense!
Simple.
We're knights in shining armor,
and he's a big bad monster.
The world will be
better once he's gone.
Trust me, it's the best way.
You can't do this!
Let's finish this once we're
on the road. Let's go.
[FURUKAWA exhales]
[KENSUKE grunts]
[tires screech]
Fukiya butchered this girl,
and her parents want
their own justice.
They asked us to help.
[KENSUKE]
By butchering him?
Hell no, we're just
delivery boys.
Though, I'm sure once they have
him they won't be satisfied
with a simple slap on the wrist.
We should get there
in seven minutes.
Ten-four.
This was supposed
to be an easy job,
but somebody got in the way.
[KENSUKE gasps]
So not good. I've gotta
shake this habit of not
following through when
it really counts, y'know?
[KENSUKE]
I know' em.
[HIDE]
Hm?
Fukiya's escorts. They aren't
cops, they're friends of mine.
For real? That's some
destiny level stuff! Crazy!
Pfft. So, uh. Your friends
are helping him, huh?
Do they throw their lot
in with murderers often?
I didn't say that!
Don't get mad.
I know what you meant.
It's just a case of both
sides being right
and both sides being wrong.
Why does everything
always end up this way?
Coincidences aside, I'm really
not all that surprised.
You have the same
smell that we do.
Say what?
[HIDE]
You know what I mean.
[KENSUKE grunts]
Stop it.
We're like birds of a feather,
drawn to each other
by our scents.
It's only natural that
we found each other.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[HIDE] That rings a bell
for you, doesn't it, Han?
[KENSUKE grunts]
[HIDE] Think about what you're
going to do once we're there.
You gonna side with your friends
or the hooligans
serving justice?
[KENSUKE grunts]
[HIDE] Hey, relax. No matter
what you decide to do,
we're not gonna
hate you or anything.
That just wouldn't
be fair, right?
For sure.
[KENSUKE exhales]
Agony.
[YOSHIO]
Throbs.
Flowers.
[YOSHIO]
Have it easy.
My, my. I didn't expect such
a poetic answer to that one.
Poetic?
[FUKIYA sighs]
It should just be another flight
or two. Let's keep moving.
Right.
[YOSHIO]
Wait.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Look.
[FUKIYA]
Hm?
[YOSHIO]
We can't. I destroyed it.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[FUKIYA laughs]
[NORO] The closest alternate
route is the west stairwell.
I'd double-time it
if I were you.
West is?
[INOUE]
This way.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[INOUE]
Of course.
Get down!
[FUKIYA]
Hm?
[FUKIYA sighs]
Let's continue, Kobayashi.
Freedom.
To find death.
So deep. I knew I liked you.
Would you shut up?
[FUKIYA]
Don't bother.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
That girl's parents.
There's no need to
cause them anymore pain.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
[FUKIYA laughs]
[NAKAMURA]
Huh?
My, my. I thought you'd
be a little more grateful
after everything I did for you!
After all. I sent
Arisu to Heaven!
[ARISU'S FATHER gasps]
[gasps]
You mean.
[FUKIYA] Bingo. Her parents.
They're down there ,too.
Probably working
with the Society.
Impossible!
Oh? Want me to prove it to you?
[INOUE gasps]
If memory serves, her daddy's
favorite dessert had just
released a brand new
flavor that day.
She looked so happy carrying
that convenience store bag.
Sweet girl. I told her my dog
had gotten away from me.
She was so concerned she
jumped at the chance to help.
[ARISU'S FATHER grunts]
Stop it! You wanna get shot?
When I told her I'd let her
go home if she obeyed,
oh, the things she did.
She even took a knife to her
ears and lopped them off!
[ARISU'S FATHER]
You bastard!
[ARISU'S FATHER grunts]
[VIGILANTE A]
Hey!
[VIGILANTE B]
Wait!
[ARISU'S FATHER]
I'm gonna kill him!
[FUKIYA chuckles]
Told you so.
[NAKAMURA]
Noro!
[NORO]
Five minutes to touchdown.
Nakamura!
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[YOSHIO gasps]
[ARISU'S FATHER grunts]
Get moving!
That was pretty bad ass.
[ARISU'S FATHER]
Fukiya!
[ARISU'S FATHER grunts]
[VIGILANTES grunt]
[ARISU'S FATHER]
Damn it!
[INOUE grunts]
[FUKIYA] Mind if I hitchhike?
My legs are exhausted.
You bastard.
Can you go any faster?
They might catch up.
[INOUE grunts]
[YOSHIO grunts]
Family.
Bunch of lies.
Prison.
A pig sty.
[FUKIYA]
Adults.
All garbage.
Embrace.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO]
Strings... No, tubes.
Mother.
[YOSHIO]
Stinks.
[FUKIYA]
Father.
[YOSHIO gasps]
The hell is this?
Ooh! My, this kid is one
special snowflake, huh?
[YOSHIO gasps]
It's not unusual for a
psychologically unstable child
to develop special
abilities over time,
but yours are a cut
above the rest, my boy.
Chat later!
You truly are a mystery, kid.
How I'd love to unravel you.
There's no mystery. If I keep
solving cases, then I can die.
You think so? I think there's
a more primitive desire at work.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[FUKIYA] They say people
develop immense strength
during a crisis.
I've experienced it myself.
Arisu displayed
astounding vitality.
[FUKIYA grunts]
Shut up!
All right. What a pity. I was
just getting to the good part.
That's enough of your drivel!
Does it sting? Protecting a
murderer like me?
[INOUE grunts]
[FUKIYA] I see and here I pegged
you for the type that was only
concerned with business.
You really love to talk.
And you have the
gall to call yourself
Akechi Kogorou's right-hand.
How pathetic.
[INOUE gasps]
Where to next, Noro?
[NORO]
Turn right at the next corner
and go past the cafeteria.
Think you boys can
shut-up long enough
for us to get
through this alive?
[FUKIYA]
Mm?
I'm not seeing a way
to rooftop from here.
Hey! What gives?
[NORO] It's a slightly
longer way around.
Go up and out the left.
Kobayashi?
[INOUE]
What's wrong?
[NAKAMURA]
You okay?
[YOSHIO gasps]
Come on, keep it together!
You're the one who accepted this
job, right? Don't quit halfway!
[YOSHIO]
Shut up.
[VIGILANTE A]
Found 'em!
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Behind me.
[FUKIYA]
Okay.
[VIGILANTE A]
Hand over that monster!
Sorry, that isn't happening.
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
If you take his side,
then you're as guilty as he is!
[VIGILANTE A]
Get ahold of yourself.
[NAKAMURA]
If we're just as guilty,
then why don't you kill us?
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
Be quiet!
[YOSHIO]
Shoot me.
[ARISU'S MOTHER gasps]
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and kill me!
[ARISU'S MOTHER whimpers]
I warned you!
[ARISU'S MOTHER gasps]
[VIGILANTE A]
What just happened?
[VIGILANTE B] The bullet.
It bounced off him.
[VIGILANTE A]
Hey!
[VIGILANTE C]
Fire!
[VIGILANTE A]
Don't back down! Kill him!
Dude! Those friends
of yours sound tough!
[VIGILANTE A]
Don't let them escape!
[KENSUKE]
Hide, I really do like you.
Aw, I like you too!
But, I...
I can't stay here.
Huh?!
He shot you down.
[HIDE sighs] That hurt more than
I expected. I'm heartbroken.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[HIDE gasps]
Hey, don't look so down, Han.
You gotta do what
you think is right.
I could never
fault you for that.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[HIDE exhales]
Fine. I'll give you a handicap.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
I mean, you're kind
of outnumbered here.
You'll get a head start of...
a hundred! Plenty of time!
After that, we won't
hold anything back.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[HIDE]
Here goes! One...!
Thanks, Hide.
[HIDE]
Two...
I'm Sorry!
[HIDE]
Three...
Four... Later, Han!
[FURUKAWA]
Hold on.
[HIDE]
Hm?
We could lose
Fukiya cause of this.
You really cool with that?
No, of course
I'm not. That said...
...I don't wanna stop Han from
helping his friends, either.
[FURUKAWA exhales]
[sighs]
Eleven...
Twelve... Thirteen...
Fourteen...
[VIGILANTE C]
What the hell is this kid?
[ARISU'S MOTHER] Use it,
while we still have a chance!
[VIGILANTE C]
We can't!
[ARISU'S MOTHER] Well then
why did we even bring it?
[VIGILANTE A] That's our ace
in hole! It's for an emergency!
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
If they get away,
this will have all
been for nothing!
Now hurry up and
blow them to pieces!
[NAKAMURA gasps]
What'd she say?
There are explosives
in that man's satchel.
Is it Semtex? Or C4?
[VIGILANTE C gasps]
[FUKIYA]
From how full the bag looks,
it would annihilate this floor.
And all of you along
with it, of course.
Are you prepared for that?
[INOUE gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[NAKAMURA grunts]
Our game was fun, Yoshio.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Hand me over to them
and you'll all get out
of here alive, Detective.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
Forget it!
I never valued my life
in the first place.
[YOSHIO]
You want to die? Why?
'Cause. I have no
attachment to this world.
[YOSHIO]
Huh...
Don't.
[YOSHIO]
I won't let you, though.
[INOUE gasps]
Detectives never quit on
a job half-way. Ever.
Well, damn. Surprising to
the end, huh?
Koba.
[INOUE chuckles]
[ARISU'S MOTHER grunts]
[VIGILANTE A]
Hey! What are doing?
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
Enough!
Give us Fukiya, or you die!
Don't test me! One press is
all it'll take to end this!
My baby, she'll finally get
the justice she's been
denied for so long.
Hand him over!
[YOSHIO]
No.
[ARISU'S MOTHER gasps]
It's my job to protect
him no matter the cost.
I can't let you
have your way, lady.
[ARISU'S MOTHER grunts]
In that case,
you'll go to hell with him!
No!
[VIGILANTE A]
Everyone retreat!
[VIGILANTES shout]
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
Die!
[gasps]
Hanasa--
Having a tough time?
[INOUE]
Boss!
I knew he'd be here.
He sure took his time.
That cocky showoff.
Bad idea. Put those down
before you get hurt.
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
Out of our way!
[ARISU'S MOTHER shouts]
[VIGILANTE A gasps]
[VIGILANTE A]
Kill'em!
[VIGILANTES grunts]
[VIGILANTE E]
Damn!
[VIGILANTE E shouts, grunts]
I'll take this. It's too
dangerous for children.
Pretty sure that's
your ride I hear, now.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
Uh.
Nakamura, quick!
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Get Fukiya up to the chopper.
Of course. Let's go.
[FUKIYA chuckles]
Good to see you, Akechi.
Yeah, yeah.
[FUKIYA] This is great. I can
keep my promise to him.
[AKECHI]
"Him"?
I have a message. Just for you.
"Welcome back.
I've been waiting for you,
Akechi, and you alone."
[AKECHI gasps]
So you're nothing but
a lowly messenger boy.
[FUKIYA]
Bye-bye.
[POLICEMAN A]
We'll arrive at the courthouse
in about seven minutes.
Be advised, the prisoner
has sustained an
injury to his abdomen.
[FUKIYA]
Hm?
[grunts]
Of course. It was only
a matter of time.
But who would have
thought that...
...the Kusakabe had someone
inside the police force.
I would rather have been,
killed by him.
Farewell, Kobayashi. It was fun.
[NAKAMURA] Huh? what do you
mean you let them get away?
[INOUE]
I'm sorry.
[NAKAMURA sighs]
[KENSUKE pants]
Kobayashi!
[NAKAMURA]
You're late, kid.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[INOUE]
The case is over.
[KENSUKE] Kobayashi. I'm sorry I
ignored all your calls. I was--
[YOSHIO]
You're here.
That means you didn't
ignore them, did you?
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[ARISU'S MOTHER]
You'll pay for this.
[ARISU'S MOTHER shouts]
[gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[YOSHIO]
It hurts.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Rebound of Break-up."