[YOSHIO gasps]
[AKECHI]
What are you doing, Kobayashi?
[YOSHIO]
Eating.
[AKECHI]
Has Inoue kept you up to speed?
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[AKECHI sighs]
Figures. Nothing's changed.
You're wrong.
[AKECHI]
Huh?
[YOSHIO]
He's changed.
[sighs]
Hanasaki? Huh?
[YOSHIO]
He's being really weird.
[AKECHI]
Hm...
[YOSHIO]
How do I fix him?
[AKECHI] You tell me.
What do you want to do?
[YOSHIO]
I guess. I want to...
...try to help him?
[AKECHI chuckles]
[YOSHIO]
Tsk
If that's the case, just do
to him what he did to you.
It's that simple.
[YOSHIO]
I don't understand.
Time's up. Sorry, kid.
--Wai--
--[busy tone]
[gasps]
♪
[GUARD A] Here you go.
Make sure they're all there.
I'll take care of it.
[GUARD B]
Hm...
[MALE VOICE laughs]
[INOUE] A route from prison
to the district court.
[NAKAMURA] Good eye. We were
going to escort the slime ball
to the court house using
this path, but there's trouble.
[NORO] Wasn't Seiji Fukiya
already sentenced
to a life-term?
It's not a re-trial.
[MIYANISHI] I'm sure you heard
about this, a Tokyo Metropolitan
Assembly member took his
car for a swim recently.
But there's evidence to
suggest that it was a murder
connected to the
Kusakabe Society.
[NORO] I thought you guys
kept running into dead-ends
as far as the Society
was concerned.
[NAKAMURA] Yes. And the fact
that the assembly member was
diagnosed with depression
doesn't help our case.
[NORO] So, what does any of this
have to do with Seiji Fukiya?
The assembly member,
Fukiya was his therapist.
[NORO]
Oh, so it was a lie?
That's the gist of it.
So we worked out a deal.
He'll testify that the Kusakabe
paid him a small fortune
to submit a false psychiatric
report and in return,
he'll get a reduced sentence.
It's obvious from the photo
that they plan to kill
Fukiya before that happens.
[INOUE]
Okay,what's our role in this?
[NAKAMURA] Guard duty.
You'll protect Fukiya.
[NORO]
Huh? Why us?
It was his own request.
He said if your firm
doesn't protect him,
then he won't testify.
[NORO] What kind of
selfish demand is that?
[NAKAMURA] No idea. Maybe he
wanted an emotional reunion
with the guy who put him away.
[NORO]
But Aka-boss isn't even here.
[INOUE]
I'm not sure we can accept.
[NAKAMURA]
Why?
[INOUE] This matter is too
serious for us to handle
while the boss is absent.
[MIYANISHI]
Hm?
--[YOSHIO grunts]
--[MIYANISHI gasps]
[YOSHIO yawns]
[MIYANISHI]
You sleep like the dead.
Tell me something. Why do you
insist on calling him "boss"
when he never does anything?
You kids solve all the cases
while he just smokes
and takes naps.
[YOSHIO]
Is this job big?
[MIYANISHI] Uh. Well, yeah.
The media's all over it.
[YOSHIO]
Then we'll take it.
[MIYANISHI, NAKAMURA]
Huh?
[NORO] We can't accept
this in Akechi's place.
He acts in his
place all the time.
[INOUE gasps]
Now I'm acting in
his place. So there.
[NORO]
What lit a fire under his butt?
[phone rings]
[FEMALE PHONE RECORDING] Sorry,
this customer is unavailable.
You may hang up, or leave
a message after the tone.
[beep]
We're protecting some criminal.
It sounded like
a job you'd like.
[YOSHIO]
Bye.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[MALE NEWSCASTER] In just a
few moments, convicted murderer,
Seiji Fukiya, will be
escorted from this prison
to testify as a
material witness.
The vehicle carrying the
prisoner is now in view!
Just look at all the
security surrounding it!
[NORO]
Overdramatic, much? Here we go!
[NORO] Now that was
as smooth as butter.
[phone rings]
[YOSHIO exhales]
[FUKIYA chuckles]
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[FUKIYA]
Know why he's not answering?
Because he doesn't want to.
[FUKIYA chuckles]
[YOSHIO grunts]
Keep your mouth shut.
By the way, had any luck
catching the group of
low-life's trying to
kill me, detective?
I didn't think so.
That's quite unsettling.
I hope three unmarked
vehicles will be enough.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
Who told you about that?
I'm simply one hell
of a psychiatrist.
One look into someone's eyes
is all I need to know
everything about them.
[FUKIYA chuckles]
[FUKIYA]
Hm?
Don't push your luck.
[FUKIYA chuckles]
--[metallic clang]
--[gasps]
--[phone rings]
[KENSUKE grunts]
--[KENSUKE gasps]
--[PUNK A laughs]
[PUNK B] Nice! Hey, let's see
if this one'll float!
--[PUNK B shouts]
--[splashing]
[PUNK A]
There, all cleaned up!
Hey, you want me to take
this crap back to car?
Nah, it's fine. Let someone
else take care of 'em.
[YOUNG WOMAN laughs]
Okay!
[grunts]
What? Problem?
You gonna lecture us?
Think you're a hero?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[PUNK A grunts]
[PUNK A, B laugh]
Heh. What a loser.
I know, right?
[PUNK A screams]
Dude! My car!
The hell did this crap
come from? It stinks!
I left my purse
in there! It's a Coach!
[HIDE] Eye for an eye, trash
for trash. Seems only fair.
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
Pretty nice work. You like?
[KENSUKE]
You did that?
[HIDE] Yep. Hit every trash
collection site I could find
and crammed it in good.
[HIDE laughs]
[HIDE]
Huh? Ugh! Man, I reek!
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[HIDE laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
You're fun. You got a name?
Oh, uh. Hansaki.
I'll call you, Han! Most folks
call me the Poser City Boy.
But my friends call me, Hide!
Got that, new friend?
Cool.
[phone rings]
[FUKIYA]
Hm...
[FEMALE PHONE RECORDING] Sorry,
this customer is unavailable.
You may hang up, or leave
a message after the tone.
[YOSHIO]
Tsk
[FUKIYA chuckles] You really
aren't normal, are you?
Fascinating.
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
I've been waiting to meet
someone just like you.
[INOUE gasps]
But in here of all places. It
exceeds my wildest expectations.
I want to know
everything about you.
Hush, creeper.
[FUKIYA]
Oh, my. Where are my manners?
I should introduce myself first.
That's only etiquette.
Since I was young. I've been
deeply interested in the
seemingly infinite variabilities
of the human psyche.
That fascination is
the sole reason
for my venture into psychiatry.
But, in the end,
it wasn't enough.
[FUKIYA] In fact,
my obsession only escalated.
I wanted to see something
far more... stimulating.
[FUKIYA]
That's when it hit me.
If death was imminent...
[GIRL PATIENT whimpers]
[FUKIYA]
...what would a person do?
[GIRL PATIENT screams]
[FUKIYA]
She was 114 years old.
The age when one's mind
is at it's most sensitive
and responsive.
I enjoyed that girl's variations
for two weeks straight.
It was intensely invigorating.
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
Especially, the climax.
The chaos before she died.
That's enough, you psycho!
Well, that's it for
my introduction.
Now, how about you?
And, please, spare no detail.
I want to know
absolutely everything.
[FUKIYA sighs] Fine, then.
Why don't we play a game?
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
Don't worry, there aren't
any complex rules.
I'll give you a series of words,
and you tell me the first thing
that pops into your mind
as quickly as you can.
See? Pure and simple.
I know this. What's it called?
Word association. Jung's test.
Indeed. He used this experiment
to solve the problems that
lurked deep within the minds
of his subjects. But not me.
[INOUE]
Huh?
I use it to learn more about the
people who pique my interests.
Shall we begin?
Fish... Green... Window...
[HIDE] I've got friends nearby.
We should go see them.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[HIDE]
Huh? What's wrong?
[KENSUKE]
I think I'll pass, after all.
[HIDE]
Why? Don't like strangers?
I'd just be a bother.
You don't want me around.
[HIDE sighs]
Y'know,
it's not up to you whether
you're a bother or not.
Let people decide
that for themselves.
[KENSUKE]
But...
[HIDE grunts]
[KENSUKE gasps]
Alright, Han. Listen good.
This is important.
The true secret of life is...
[stomach growls]
[KENSUKE]
Uh...
[HIDE chuckles]
[HIDE] Well, there ya have it.
Glad we had this talk.
[FURUKAWA]
Hm?
[HIDE]
Yo!
Great, you found
another one.
Don't mind him, Han.
He may put the hooligan in
"Hide and the Hooligans",
but he's really a big softie.
[FURUKAWA grunts]
Look, I've told you!
For the hundredth time.
I'm not the "Hooligan".
My name is "Red Beetle",
ya got that?
[HIDE laughs] You hear that?
What a goofy name.
"Red Beetle"!
Well, "Hide and the Hooligans"
makes us sound like
a crappy punk band.
[HIDE]
Huh? Whatchu talkin' bout?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Set this loser
straight for me.
"Hide and the Hooligans"
is way cooler sounding, right?
Uh...
[FURUKAWA] In your dreams,
Red Beetle is cooler.
Oh, uh... Hm.
There. Ya see that?
Han's such a friendly guy he's
staying neutral so he doesn't
have to deal a death
blow to your fragile ego.
I think Red Bettle's better.
Yup. That's what I thought.
No way!
Yours sounds dorky.
[FURUKAWA] You didn't
sugarcoat it. Respect.
[HIDE] I'll never give
it to you now, Hans.
[KENSUKE]
Uh...
It was a "Hide and
the Hooligans"
tanktop with your
name on it, traitor!
[HIDE sobs, yells]
[KENSUKE]
Wait!
What the hell.
So, d'you get into some
kinda trouble, too?
[KENSUKE grunts]
I thought so. Well, you've come
to the right place.
All the guys here have
screwed up one way or another
and dropped out of normal
society. Including me.
We're strays. The only kind
of people Hide takes in.
What about him?
The worst of the bunch.
[FURUKAWA] He's a scumbag.
Been in and out of juvie
so many times, they probably
have a cell set aside for him.
Scumbag...
Want a treat?
I made Bavarian Cream!
You're kidding!
Your timing sucks.
He was about to tell me what
kinda trouble he's caused.
[HIDE]
Who cares? The past is the past!
Everyone screws
up eventually, don't they?
Let's forget about
it and enjoy life!
Starting with this
Bavarian Cream.
Here!
Thanks, it looks really tasty.
Well? Good, right?
I made it myself!
I came up with the
recipe specifically
for our little party!
So, whaddya think?
[KENSUKE chuckles]
What? What is it?
[KENSUKE laughs] Is this
really Bavarian Cream?
What'd you say?
[FURUKAWA]
Saw that coming.
I nailed it this time!
[HIDE gasps, grunts]
[HIDE]
It's so bland!
[FURUKAWA]
Of course it is!
It tastes like tofu!
[KENSUKE laughs]
[HIDE] That's it! No seconds
for you! I'm serious!
[ALL laugh]
Murder... Head...
[FUKIYA sighs] Well, at least
I know you're stubborn.
[INOUE grunts]
I hope I get to know
the real you soon.
--[alarm buzzes]
--[NORO] Huh?
[NORO]
Huh?
[NORO] Guys, you went off route
after that last intersection.
[INOUE]
What? Okay, I'll check on it.
Something wrong?
Driver! Why'd you turn?
Hey! Answer me! Dammit!
[ALL grunt]
[NAKAMURA] Don't think
I like that answer.
[gasps] Why'd they
suddenly speed up?
Looks like it's beginning.
[YOSHIO grunts]
Bullet-proof glass?
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[phone buzzes]
[MIYANISHI] What's this about?
Why the sudden rush?
[NAKAMURA] Miyanishi, can you
stop this van somehow?
[gasps] Sure, hold tight.
I'll try to pit--
[MIYANISHI]
What the hell?
[MIYANISHI yells]
[MIYANISHI groans]
Nakamura.
Are you there? What happened?
Miyanishi? Talk to me!
Don't take another step!
You're excited
about this, aren't you?
I can see it in your eyes.
Huh?
[FUKIYA]
You're thrilled. Don't lie.
Not really. It's just. I like
the flashy cases most of all.
[YOSHIO grunts]
No way! Did...
Koba actually get hurt?
[YOSHIO grunts]
Tsk.
Move it.
Ah-ha!
Koba, don't do it.
Are you out of your mind?
[PIPPO hoots]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[NAKAMURA grunts] What the
hell is going on here?
Could you warn us
next time? It's not hard!
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[sighs]
What a disaster.
Who asked you?
--[car engine rumbles]
--[YOSHIO, INOUE] Hm?
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[DETECTIVE A]
Detective Nakamura!
You're not hurt, are you?
[NAKAMURA] We're fine.
What happened to Miyanishi?
He was rendered immobile while
we were chasing down the van.
Just some minor cuts
and bruises, though.
[NAKAMURA] I see.
[DETECTIVE A] We can take
Fukiya from here. Please.
[NAKAMURA]
No. I'm seeing this one through.
Heh. Not this time, ma'am.
We don't have room for you.
[gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
What is this?
[INOUE gasps]
Heads up, Nakamura!
[DETECTIVE B shouts]
[NAKAMURA]
Move it!
[DETECTIVE A grunts]
[YOSHIO grunts]
The hell?
What's with this kid?
Man! That's one helluva feast.
[KENSUKE]
So, what is this party for?
Huh? Oh wait, I didn't tell you?
[FURUKAWA]
Hide.
[HIDE]
Huh?
Plan B. It's time to move.
[HIDE sighs]
Man.
What's wrong?
Nothin'. Just gonna relocate.
The party's venue
has been changed.
Uh...
Ideas? I'm fresh out of 'em!
Koba!
[gasps]
All right!
[NAKAMURA grunts] Get up!
Do you wanna die out here?
[FUKIYA] Might as well.
Unless Kobayashi plays my game
with me. I'm not moving.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[NAKAMURA]
Get over it!
I have no desire to shove off
this mortal coil. Trust me.
Well, Kobayashi. Looks like
our fates are in your hands.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO]
You just want me to play?
[FUKIYA]
That's right.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[NORO]
Koba! Don't!
[FUKIYA laughs]
Then let's play.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES] "Regenisis of
the Beast in the Shadows."