[KENSUKE] Nice! And after
his fourth fall of the day,
Kobayashi has no injuries,
no blood loss,
and still isn't dead!
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
[KENSUKE] And that's the eighth
tongue click of the day!
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Want some help?
Just hurry and pull me up.
Okay, you heard the man.
[pants]
[KENSUKE] C'mon. Why not
live at Akechi's place?
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE] You'd never go
hungry there, for one thing.
It's cleaner, too.
Get out of my room.
It's so unstable.
Don't touch it.
Stop filming. Leave.
But there's nothing to do.
I'm freakin' bored here.
[KENSUKE] Akechi was all "I need
a break after yesterday",
then took off without telling
us where he was going.
Inoue's at school.
And Noro's being Noro.
There's just nothing to do.
Except for playing around
with you, of course!
[YOSHIO]
Think about it.
Huh?
You know, me.
[KENSUKE]
Oh! That! Right! Later.
I knew it. You're not
serious about this.
Sure I am! Totally serious!
[YOSHIO scoffs]
[KENSUKE]
I'm thinking about it, okay?
It's just not... that easy.
Uh.
[chuckles]
♪
[INOUE]
Requests?
[KENSUKE] Yeah! You know, jobs!
The ones the boss deleted.
I accepted six.
Take care of them!
[gasps]
What do expect to accomplish
without the boss around?
[KENSUKE]
It's fine, trust me.
--He's so handsome.
--[INOUE] I can't do that.
[KENSUKE] Chill out!
I can solve them.
[INOUE]
Based on what?
Stop yelling at me!
It's not helping, bro.
[INOUE] I yell because you
make the same mistakes.
Don't worry. That won't happen
this time. Koboayashi will help.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[WALLA: STUDENTS]
Just the two of you?
[KENSUKE] What? You don't
think we can handle it?
You're underestimating us,
Inoue.
Try not to cause any trouble.
[KENSUKE]
So, you're saying it's okay?
Just know I won't help you.
[KENSUKE] Roger that. You've got
exams coming up, right?
So do you, moron.
Yes!
You lied to me.
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
I only came along with
you because you said you'd
find a way for me to die.
[KENSUKE] You're right,
I did. This'll do that!
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
I've got a theory. Remember the
times you got hurt?
[KENSUKE] First at the factory,
then at the venue hall.
Both after you helped someone.
So if we solve a bunch of cases,
you can get hurt a bunch
of times and finally
kick the bucket!
[YOSHIO sighs]
Come on. You could try
to be enthusiastic.
It sounds shady.
Hello, pot, meet kettle.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Forget about it.
Anyway, I've given this some
serious thought for once.
You should take
it seriously, too.
[YOSHIO]
Hm.
Hm?
Okay. First job.
We need to get another
vase like this one.
Are you serious?
As death. The client must
really like the thing.
[gasps]
There!
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[KENSUKE] Come on, dude,
this is our chance!
Sometimes I even amaze myself.
What is this place, exactly?
Just wait. You'll see.
[doorbell rings]
[footsteps]
[PIPPO hoots]
Ah! No! Shoo!
Quit it, Pippo!
[KENSUKE grunting]
I told you to put
in an application
before coming over here.
Uh?
Uh. Who are you?
[NORO] Huh? You don't smell as
bad as I thought you would.
[NORO sighs]
[YOSHIO]
Huh? Grass?
[NORO] Lemon balm
and mint, you savage.
[KENSUKE] Blech. This stuff
smells like garbage juice.
[NORO grunts]
[NORO]
Now, why are you here?
You know I've got hot
yoga at two o'clock.
[KENSUKE]
This won't take you that long.
[NORO] Even a paramecium-brain
like you should be able to toss
that into a 3D printer.
True, but this thing's
pretty valuable.
I didn't wanna break it.
[NORO grunts]
Oh! While you're here.
[NORO] I need you to
fill this out for me.
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
It's our member list. You are
technically a member now, so...
Uh?
Oh, you mean his profile?
Sorry. No can do.
He doesn't know
anything about himself.
Even your age?
You heard him.
Or your birthplace?
Don't know it.
Or your birthday?
Don't care to.
What?! You poor thing.
That's tragic!
Why?
[NORO]
'Cause it's your birthday!
The one day a
year you're a star!
You get gifts from people!
Doesn't that sound nice?
Not especially, no.
[NORO]
He's crazy.
Hey. Can we ditch this weirdo?
[KENSUKE]
All right!
While that thing's printing,
let's head out to the next job!
[YOSHIO]
Oh, right.
Can't you two sit still
for a few minutes?
It won't take that long!
[NORO]
Hm?
Wow! He's the real deal.
[exhales]
Did'ja think I was
pulling your chain?
It wouldn't be the first
time you've exaggerated.
C'mon, this is me talkin'.
So this is the second job?
I'm gettin' there.
Keep your shirt on.
My client was told that
nobody could fix it.
[OHTOMO]
Hm... A challenge.
Ah, I see.
Looks like the problem is
with the contact, here.
[KENSUKE gasps]
Their clothes are a weird color.
Hey, I happen to like gray.
Couldn't say why. Do you
have a favorite color?
Sky blue, huh?
I didn't expect that.
[YOSHIO]
Tsk. Cause you're dumb.
There. That should do it.
[KENSUKE]
Already?
[OHTOMO] I added some
extra features, too.
What kinda features?
He's open!
[BOTH gasp]
[YAMANE gasps]
What... was that?
[KENSUKE]
Oh, no. Don't freak out.
[OHTOMO]
That's his normal reaction.
[YAMANE] Come on. Don't add
weird functions to those things!
[BOTH]
Hm?
There's nothing funny
about a boomerang
with a self-destruct feature!
Sorry about that. Are you hurt?
Tsk. I wish that
was the case.
O...kay. Whatever.
So, uh. How do we handle him?
For now, at least, we'll let him
believe it was the boomerang.
--[phone buzzes]
--[INOUE gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Hey! Don't ignore me !
Good. Katsuta's here, too!
[KATSUTA]
Shh!
Oh, right, my bad.
[KENSUKE]
What? You like pizza?
Maybe. I've never
had any before.
What are you doing here?
Oh, just droppin' in
since I was around.
[Isighs] I'm guessing you
haven't given up, then?
Not on your life, man.
We're just five minutes away
from having two cases solved.
With help from Noro
and Ohtomo. That right?
Uh.
[INOUE] I thought you
said the two of you
would handle them alone.
Don't be such a stiff, man.
You'll die young.
[INOUE] So you can't
even keep one promise.
[KENSUKE groans]
Chill.
You chose to accept the jobs.
You can finish them your own.
Jeez. Alright.
We'll do all of the deducing
and solving ourselves. Right?
One question. How do we do that?
No clue.
[INOUE sighs] Kensuke, how long
have you been a detective?
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[phone buzzes]
[MAN A]
You rock, my man.
--[mp3 player beeps]
--[cheers]
Thank you for choosing
the Boy Detective's--
[MAN A]
Hold up.
Hey! What the hell is this?
Security?
[yawns]
I'm here to deliver the
vase you asked for.
[OLD WOMAN]
Hm? Excuse me?
Uh?
[OLD WOMAN] What were you trying
to do with my vase, young lady?
[WOMAN B]
Mother, please, calm down.
[OLD WOMAN] You were going to
sell the original and leave me
with this piece
of junk, weren't you?
[WOMAN B]
Of course not!
[OLD WOMAN] My son works hard
for you, you ungrateful jezebel!
[WOMAN B]
That's it!
Uh, ma'am? I need to
collect my commission fee.
[gasps]
Another failure.
[KENSUKE]
Welp. Let's move on!
[YOSHIO]
Don't you feel bad?
[KENSUKE] We don't have
time for that crap.
[YOSHIO]
I see.
We'll handle the rest of the
jobs by ourselves this time!
[KENSUKE groans]
So? What's the last one about?
Some lovers quarrel.
That's stupid.
Come on, don't say that.
Let's just get it
done and go home.
Tsk.
Don't like rain?
The roof always leaks.
The Ferris wheel car?
[YOSHIO]
Mm-hm.
Like I said. You could
just move in with Akechi.
Why don't you?
There's a bed available!
Bed's don't work for me.
Huh?
If I'm not in the car,
I can't fall asleep.
Really?
You're such a liar!
[yelps]
Tsk.
[footsteps]
Here she comes.
We're oh and five,
let's make this one a win.
[YOSHIO grunts]
A little team work and we'll
kick this job in the ass.
Shut up and walk.
[KENSUKE]
Okay. Once she's in the car,
we'll sneak up and snap
a few candids of them.
That'll be all the proof
we need to call this a day.
Uh...
[YOSHIO]
Hey.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Hey.
[MAN B, WOMAN B]
Huh?
You cheating?
[WOMAN B gasps]
Looks like it.
[KENSUKE sighs]
You want to say it's all
my fault, don't you?
Not at all. I was
gonna say I'm sorry.
What?
I still wasn't able
to keep my promise.
[YOSHIO grunts]
Tough day. Six jobs and we
couldn't finish one of 'em.
It was impossible. We needed
help from the others.
At least we tried.
Huh?
I wanna complete
some jobs with you,
and this was good practice.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[glass shatters]
[BOY A]
Uh-oh.
[KENSUKE, YOSHIO]
Uh, hm?
[BOY B grunts]
What do we do? My brother's
gonna kill me for sure!
Sorry, man. No clue.
Come on!
Guess I got no choice.
[YOSHIO]
Uh?
[KENSUKE grunts]
This'll only take a minute!
[YOSHIO exhales]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[BOY B grunts]
Come on!
[BOY A]
It's gone, bro.
Fly, dammit!
Why won't you work?
[KENSUKE gasps]
[grunts]
[YOSHIO]
Tsk. He's taking forever.
[BOY B sobs]
[BOY 6A]
Quit crying.
Tell you what,
I'll apologize with you.
Do you mean it?
I know I wouldn't want
to do it all alone.
[YOSHIO grunts]
Hey!
[BOY A]
Uh?
[YOSHIO]
Wait there.
Hm.
[gasps, shouts]
[grunts] Son of a-- I'm gonna
feel that in the morning.
[grunts]
Where'd it go?
Aw! Give me a break!
[gasps]
[KENSUKE gasps]
[grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi! Kobayashi!
[gasps]
Hurry and pull me out of here.
[laughs]
[BOYS chuckles]
Be careful getting home, okay?
Now we're six and one.
You good?
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
Did you get injured?
No.
What the hell?!
Huh?
It doesn't make any sense.
You helped someone
and didn't die.
Whatever.
When you fell in the furnace,
I thought you were
dead for sure. Crazy.
I've tested blast furnaces.
They don't work either.
Awesome!
Did you say "I'll be back"?
Why would I do that?
[KENSUKE]
Damn, it's this late already?
[YOSHIO]
Mm?
[KENSUKE] I bet you're hungry.
Let's go eat.
[YOSHIO]
Sure.
[KENSUKE]
You go on ahead.
[YOSHIO]
Okay.
[clapping]
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[ALL]
Happy Birthday, Kobayashi!
And many more.
Huh?
Uh...
[KENSUKE] You said you didn't
know when you were born,
so we decided...
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
...from now on, today will
be your birthday.
[NORO] I was getting everything
ready while you two were running
around playing
detective all day.
Hanasaki can pull off
some elaborate schemes
when he puts his mind to it.
I know. You're so emotional
you can't even speak.
Don't flatter yourself.
You can't just decide this.
[INOUE]
No!
Cake comes after you
blow out the candles.
He's right.
But, before that, you gotta
open up your birthday present!
Huh?
[KENSUKE]
This way!
[YOSHIO]
Hm...
[KENSUKE]
Drumroll...
Ta-da!
[gasps]
Now I know you're speechless!
I am. Why are you so proud
when you did nothing?
We're the ones who
did all the work.
He's right, you know. Do you
have any idea how many
round trips it took to
move this thing here?
[KENSUKE laughs]
Sorry about that.
[YOSHIO] All you ever do is
cause trouble for people.
[OHTOMO]
Now, now.
[YAMANE] He's such a
freakin' slave driver.
Now that you're here,
we're roomies!
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Happy Birthday, Kobayashi.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[OHTOMO] Let's go inside
and eat. I'm starving.
[YAMANE]
Kensuke, you don't get any cake.
[NORO]
Do I get cake?
Hey! Do I get cake?
Are you having fun on
your first birthday?
Not really.
Too bad.
[OHTOMO] Hey, aren't these
chairs backwards?
[KENSUKE] Don't sweat
the small stuff, man.
[NORO]
I better get cake!
[YOSHIO chuckles]
[YAMANE]
Are there enough drinks?
They could have saved
a slice, at least.
[wings flapping]
[PIPPO hoots]
[NORO giggling]
Pippo!
[YOSHIO snores]
[gnat buzzes]
[KENSUKE]
Mm?
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE]
I knew you'd like it.
I'm home.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Pure Trist."