[TWENTY-FACES] Since the day
mankind began to dig graves,
offer flowers, and mourn the
deaths of those around them...
...all 110 billion people who
have ever lived on this planet,
have perished,
one way or another.
[TWENTY-FACES] And the six point
nine billion still living today,
you know, the ones who
bravely tread the ground
in which the dead
peacefully sleep...
[GIRL A screams]
[TWENTY-FACES] ...will one
day join them, and rot.
[TWENTY-FACES]
And not just humans.
Every form of life is destined
to wind up in death's embrace.
[GIRL A screams]
[PUNK A]
Hey! Grab her legs!
[TWENTY-FACES]
Yet most of them do not realize
that death is a gift
bestowed upon the living.
[GIRL A grunts]
[PUNK B groans]
[TWENTY-FACES]
For death is rest.
A mirror, vividly reflecting
one's life, without prejudice.
[growls]
Damn you!
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[PUNK A grunting]
[grunts]
Oh, did that hurt?
Well, that just means
you're still alive.
How 'bout some more?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[grunts]
[screams]
[KENSUKE] If anything
else happens to you,
well-- here's hoping
nothing will-- but,
If it does, come see me.
[GIRL A]
The Boy Detectives' Club?
[chuckles]
[YOSHIO inhales]
I want to die.
♪
[CROWD chatters]
[radio plays]
[MAN A]
Loud much? Damn.
[GIRL B] What the heck?
That's hilarious!
[YOUNG GIRL A]
Huh?
[CROWD shouts]
[AKECHI]
Ba... Ba... Ba...
Bazooka!
Armalite Carbine.
[AKECHI]
E. Enarm MMG.
Glock pistol.
"L"? Really?
That's way too easy.
Give me something harder.
You know you want to.
[AKECHI]
Let's see. Lercker!
[INOUE]
Ruby.
[AKECHI gasps]
Y.
It's Detective Nakamura.
[AKECHI]
Mm.
Yes? Akechi Investigation
Firm here.
[NAO] Got a job for you,
Master Detective.
[AKECHI]
The robot in Shibuya?
[NAO]
Wow, you get news fast.
[AKECHI] Work's the only
thing I do fast, sweetheart.
[NAO]
Uh...
[INOUE]
Almost there.
Just 500 meters.
Wait! Where are you--
[ALL gasp]
Don't worry, Detective.
I'll take care of
your robot problem.
There's a 30 percent surcharge.
Of course. If you like,
you can pay with that
tight little body of yours.
[NAO grunts]
[AKECHI]
Hm!
[AKECHI grunts]
[INOUE] Hey, please set your
phone to answer on opening.
Yeah, yeah.
[AKECHI]
What about the kid?
[INOUE]
Hanasaki?
He's got a different toy
to play with today.
[KENSUKE pants]
[NORO] Are you getting what
they call a "runner's high"?
Nope, no high for me.
[NORO] Still, you're a hardcore
adrenaline junkie.
Both excesses and
deficiencies of adrenaline
can shorten your lifespan.
Oh, give it a rest, Noro.
[NORO exhales]
Whatever.
If you don't find it today,
you can kiss your fee goodbye.
[KENSUKE] I'm lookin', okay?
Gimme a break.
[NORO]
Okay, take the next right.
[KENSUKE]
Got it!
[NORO]
Not that way! I said right!
Like the hand you
hold chopsticks with!
Or the side that
conservatives are on!
--Not the Ise Expressway!
--[phone rings]
[AKECHI]
Noro, you're up!
[NORO giggles]
Yes, sir!
Two-oh-two-oh-oh-seven-two-four.
Getting in on the
Olympic fever? Nice.
[NORO] I won't hack
the inside, though.
I get the feeling I don't want
to make enemies of these people.
Don't worry 'bout it,
I can take things from here.
[OPERATOR A] We're checking
the log-in records, but there's
no sign of who
last used it.
[OPERATOR C] The excavator
just reached the utility duct.
[OPERATOR D]
It hit the cable!
[OPERATOR E]
It's trying to invade--
[MALE OPERATOR 1B]
I know that! Put up a firewall!
But, sir, if we isolate
the main system,
we'll lose all control
of the security network--
[OPERATOR B]
Just do it!
Right.
What the hell?
Pretty fancy trap
you've set up.
Using the robot as a decoy
while you personally
breach the system.
What exactly are you trying
to put in the main computer?
[chuckles]
Rather talkative today,
aren't we, Akechi? It's cute.
And you did a poor job of
following through today,
Fiend with Twenty Faces.
[OPERATOR B]
Did he say Twenty-Faces?
[OPERATOR C screams]
[AKECHI] So, when'd you
bust out of prison?
[TWENTY-FACES] Was I sent
to prison? I don't recall that.
[screams]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[AKECHI grunts]
[AKECHI sighs] Looks like we're
playing hide and seek, now.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[NORO] Jeez, there's no point
in being your navigator.
[KENSUKE] Would you relax?
I found this, now didn't I?
[KENSUKE] That means
Melodina must be hiding
somewhere around here, right?
There's no way
it'll be that easy.
[KENSUKE]
Found her!
What?!
[MELODINA pants]
[KENSUKE]
Melodina.
Time to go home!
Come back!
Stupid dog!
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
[AKECHI]
I know, Inoue. I blew it.
[INOUE] If you didn't know that,
we'd have a big problem.
Well?
Any idea where he went?
Wait. I'm recalling the
facilities' structure.
There are three escape routes
out of the control room.
The shortest would be
out of the south exit
and into the waterway,
but I can't imagine this guy
using such an obvious path.
It's also very likely that he
was expecting you to show up.
That said, There's only
one place he'd go.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
The robot that suddenly appeared
in Shibuya is said to be
the next generation of
security bots, under development
by Hinomoto Heavy Industries.
No further informa--
You certainly took
your time, Akechi.
[AKECHI]
Yeah, well,
punctuality and I have
never really gotten along.
[MAN C] You still carry that
dangerous thing around
in public, "Master Detective"?
[chuckles]
What an evil man you are.
[WAITER A]
Sorry for the wait.
Assam Tea. Your favorite, yes?
[MELODINA pants, barks]
[KENSUKE grunt, groans]
Gimme a break!
[NORO] Just grab her!
It's almost time for my Pilates.
You can do that stuff anytime,
Little Miss Shut-In.
[NORO gasps] Hey, you're not
allowed to say that!
That's moral harassment, buddy!
[NORO gasps]
[NORO screams]
[MELODINA barks]
[KENSUKE]
Come here, you stupid mutt!
Uh!
[barks]
Huh?
[barking continues]
[YOSHIO whimpers]
Uh, hello there. What's up?
[YOSHIO]
Leave!
[whimpers]
It's all right. I'm just
here to catch the dog.
Then I'll be out of your hair.
[MELODINA barks]
Hey! Idiot!
[YOSHIO whimpers]
Stay back!
[MELODINA yelps]
[whimpers]
[YOSHIO] Dammit, why?
I told you... to stay away.
I told you!
[YOSHIO whimpers]
I...
I did nothing wrong!
[gasps]
Hey, wait!
[KENSUKE gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Hm! You're kidding!
[explosions]
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
We're not sure why,
but now the robot is launching
a barrage of fireworks.
Pretty fancy show you're
putting on out there.
What would you like
for the finale?
I have explosives,
or poison gas if you prefer.
You trying to threaten me?
[MAN C] Or, we could call
it a draw for today.
[gasps]
Your tea is ready.
[YOSHIO groans]
--[gunshot]
--[YOSHIO gags, coughs]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[YOSHIO]
Just let me die!
[NORO]
What? That doesn't make sense!
[INOUE sighs] Look. If you don't
get it now, you're not going to.
[NORO] But to retract their
request like that, it's just--
Drop it. Just tell Hanasaki
he doesn't have to look
for the dog anymore.
[NORO]
But...
[INOUE] You're the one who
said you'd look after him, Noro.
Am I right?
[NORO gasps]
[NORO] I don't have to take
this kind of crap from you!
That's bullying...!
[AKECHI] Would you keep
it down, please?
I swear. Sometimes it feels like
I'm running a daycare center.
Huh?
[PIPPO hoots]
[NAO grunts]
All that work,
and it didn't even
have explosives in it.
There didn't need to be.
Twenty-Faces knew we'd
have to focus on the robot.
[NAO gasps]
It isn't fair.
We should have
jurisdiction here.
Security bots are
top-secret tech.
You know that.
"We'll be sure to look
into it." Yeah, right.
[DOG barks]
[KENSUKE gasps]
[YOUNG BOY]
Aww! So cute!
[KENSUKE] You're sadder than
anyone about it, aren't you?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE gasps]
Wait!
[exhales]
[KENSUKE]
That won't work this time!
[gasps]
[KENSUKE grunts]
Stay back!
[KENSUKE chuckles]
Whoa!
[gasps]
[KENSUKE grunts, groans]
[KENSUKE]
Jeez, that hurts.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[gasps]
Just leave me alone!
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE laughs]
Nice one!
[YOSHIO] Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it, stop it!
[YOSHIO pants]
[YOSHIO gasps]
Huh?
[gasps]
[YOSHIO exhales]
[KENSUKE] You love diving
into stuff, don't you?
[YOSHIO]
Please stop.
If you get any closer,
you'll die.
[KENSUKE grunts]
Hold that thought.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Do you want cider or tea?
[YOSHIO gasps]
Cool. Tea it is.
[KENSUKE yelps]
[KENSUKE grunts, chuckles]
So cool. You crack me up.
Huh?
[KENSUKE]
Go on. Take a big gulp.
[bottle hisses]
[coughs]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Like it?
Never had it before. It's good.
So, uh. What's with
the crazy force field?
If I knew the answer
to that, I'd stop it.
I see. It's something you
have no control over, then.
But you can't die.
That's awesome!
It's not awesome!
[KENSUKE gasps]
[YOSHIO] You don't get it.
Death is the only thing I want.
[gasps]
Sorry! Gotta go!
I'll see you next time!
What's his deal?
[gasps]
[KENSUKE] We aren't in
the clear yet, Noro!
[NORO] Slow down!
You're not making any sense!
[KENSUKE] The robot case that
popped up earlier today.
Twenty-Faces is planning
something major, I'm sure of it!
A fire at Hinomoto Heavy
Industries at a time like this?
[NORO]
Planning what, exactly?
[INOUE]
We're on our way. Wait for us.
[KENSUKE chuckles]
Not my style!
--[INOUE] Idiot!
--[AKECHI] That boy.
[NORO]
He's totally holding a grudge.
Remind me. What did you
do to deserve payment?
[AKECHI chuckles]
[OPERATORS shouting]
[NORO]
He's definitely a junkie.
[INOUE] Keep the trace
on Hanasaki. Don't lose him!
[NORO] Dumb thrill seeker.
He's gonna die young!
Why am I doing this for him?
[KENSUKE] Hang on.
We're almost there.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NORO]
Oh, no. It just stopped.
[INOUE]
I can see that.
[NORO]
Not you. Hanasaki's tracer.
He's not here.
[OPERATOR E]
Hey!
Help me!
[gasps]
We don't have much time! Hurry!
Hey! Are you deaf? Help me!
[YOSHIO]
Sorry, I can't.
[OPERATOR E gasps]
Screw you, freakin' brat! Die!
[gasps]
[OPERATOR E pants]
[KENSUKE grunts]
You came here to
rescue me, didn't you?
You know I can't do that.
You've seen it.
Still. You tried,
and that's what matters.
We're gonna push on
the count of three.
One... Two...
Three!
[KENSUKE, OPERATOR E grunting]
[KENSUKE]
Was worried for a sec.
[OPERATOR E yelps]
[OPERATOR E] Stay away
from me, freak! I mean it!
You damn brat!
Monster! Drop dead!
Lay down and burn like
the demon you are!
That's all that I've
been trying to do!
[scoffs] Then do it!
Think I care? I don't! At all!
Die, die, die, die, die!
[grunts]
[OPERATOR E gasps]
[KENSUKE] Keep acting up,
and I'll leave you here.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE chuckles]
Just kidding!
But save your tantrum until
we're out of here, okay?
Now, then.
Since you're here,
wanna help a bit more?
[KENSUKE]
Whoa! So freakin' cool!
You really are invincible!
[OPERATOR E pants]
[OPERATOR E]
Damn brats!
[KENSUKE] Hey! A little
appreciation wouldn't hurt ya!
Jerk. Seriously, some people
are just impossible to please.
[KENSUKE]
Hey.
[gasps]
Join me. Become a member of
the Boy Detective's Club.
[KENSUKE] Together, we could
protect the people of this city.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[KENSUKE]
And as a sign-on bonus,
I promise I'll find a
way to grant your wish.
No matter what it takes.
One day, I'll kill you.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[YOSHIO shouts]
[KENSUKE gasps] Oh wow,
you shriek like a girl.
[KENSUKE]
Does it hurt?
[KENSUKE] That's just
proof that you're still alive.
[KENSUKE laughs]
[KENSUKE]
Man, you really crack me up!
[laughing continues]
[KENSUKE]
Oh yeah. I never got your name.
Yoshio... Kobayashi.
I see. So, Kobayashi,
wanna be my partner in fight--
[KENSUKE grunts]
Hanasaki!
[YOSHIO gasps]
Get away from him, now!
Put the gun down, Inoue.
It's not what it looks like.
Damn. Idiot!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
No. Make it stop!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[yells]
[AKECHI]
Um...
Nao, dear?
[NAO] Give it a rest.
That's all you're getting.
You want more, do something
I can take credit for.
[AKECHI] Man, future police
commissioners are scary.
[NAO] So, any idea what
Twenty-Faces is after this time?
[AKECHI] There'll be a separate
fee for that investigation.
[groans]
Okay. Refund me
for the first one.
I was just joshin' ya!
Come on, Nao... Smile!
Eh? Eh...?
[20
"Hinomoto Heavy Industries
ordered to suspend
operations indefinitely."
[20 chuckles]
Things are really going
to get fun now, Akechi.
[YOSHIO exhales]
[YOSHIO]
It tingles.
[TWENTY-FACES]
"The Golden Traker."