[INOUE]
Kobayashi! Hey! Dammit.
How many times have I told
you not to act on your own?
[gasps]
[INOUE]
Stop and think!
Hanasaki is probably up there.
The way things are looking,
Twenty-Faces has complete
control over the security
system. We need a pl--
[KATSUTA grunts]
[gasps]
[KENSUKE grunts]
Who said you could move?
Next time, you'll get a bullet.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Ha.
[AKECHI grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES]
All the actors are in place.
♪
[NORO grunts]
[NORO]
Dammit!
[OHTOMO]
Throwing a hissy fit
isn't gonna make the
jamming go away.
[NORO groans]
You can mash the keys all day.
It won't work. Sorry.
The robots' operating systems
are out of reach, for now.
[NORO]
Hm? For now? What?
[OHTOMO]
Come on, Noro.
I thought you were
smarter than this.
[NORO growls]
There's work to be done.
I don't have time to babysit.
Did... you just... call me..
I am not a baby!
You... You... stupid jerk face!
[MALE STAFF A]
Someone!
Help us!
[MALL STAFF chatter]
More hostages.
[gasps]
How many?
[KATSUTA]
Around twenty.
And three security bots.
[KATSUTA]
Think we can?
Do you think we
have a choice?
[NAKAMURA]
I'm telling you...
...nothing is going
on at the complex!
Le Waqua's security system says
everything is in the green.
[NORO] And I'm telling you
it's a total mess in there!
[NAKAMURA]
The word of a child isn't enough
to justify police action!
If something blew up,
it'd be a different story.
[MIYANISHI] Cool it.
Don't take your anger out on her
just cause you
miss your boyfriend.
[NAKAMURA]
You wanna die?
[growls]
[phone buzzes]
[YOSHIO pants]
[YOSHIO]
Where are you? Hey!
You're such a pain
in the ass, man.
Why am I doing this for you?
[YOSHIO]
Quit ignoring me!
Hey! Hanasaki!
[YOSHIO gasps]
[gasps]
[KATSUTA grunts]
[INOUE]
Got you!
[KATSUTA grunts]
Now's your chance!
Get out of here!
[MALL STAFF gasp]
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
[TWENTY-FACES] I expected no
less from your right-hand man.
Impressive.
[AKECHI]
What about me?
[TWENTY-FACES]
Hm.
[AKECHI]
I'm the one you're after.
Let's get this
over with already.
[TWENTY-FACES] Hm. Not yet.
We have another visitor.
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi. You came, too?
[TWENTY-FACES] Hello.
It's good to see you again.
Well, Kensuke? He has come
all this way to save you.
You could say something.
[YOSHIO]
Stop it!
[TWENTY-FACES]
Mm.
Stop changing. I can't keep up!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[YOSHIO pants]
[YOSHIO] You laugh...
then get mad or cry.
[YOSHIO pants]
Pull yourself together!
And as for you...
[AKECHI]
Hm?
You're too damn weak.
[AKECHI]
Hmph. Whatever.
[YOSHIO] I'll say it once.
If you're okay with looking like
such a lame-ass,
then you should just...
"Just die already."
[YOSHIO grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Right?
Don't lie.
We both know his death is
the last thing you want.
So then--
How about Akechi?
Or your other friends?
[KENSUKE]
Please, stop.
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
You can't make me.
You won't even try.
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
Think they're weak?
You're exactly like them.
Say what?
[TWENTY-FACES] That's the price
of being part of a group.
Understand?
I couldn't understand
someone like you.
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
Then what are you going to do?
[YOSHIO gasps]
Well. Hanasaki?
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
What do... you want to do?
[KENSUKE gasps]
Silence is your answer?
How disappointing.
--[alarm blares]
--[KENSUKE gasps]
[YOSHIO]
No!
[SECURITY ROBOT A]
Boing. Boing. Boing.
[INOUE, KATSUTA gasp]
[SECURITY ROBOTS]
Boing. Boing. Boing...
Pippo!
Nicely done, Noro.
[NORO] Sadly, I can't
take credit for this.
I was useless without him.
[INOUE]
Huh?
Today's MVP goes to...
Ohtomo and his crazy drones!
Canceling a signal
jam's a piece of cake.
You can thank me later.
[SECURITY ROBOTS]
Boing. Boing. Boing.
And now... to get the
police's attention! Boom!
[footsteps]
[AKECHI grunts]
It's over. Come quietly.
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
I'll pass.
[TWENTY-FACES]
This is only the beginning,
dear Akechi.
[INOUE, KATSUTA gasp]
[gasps]
Late as usual.
Should have known.
[police sirens blaring]
[YUMEKO gasps]
Wait, isn't that?
[NORO]
What? Why's the signal gone?
[OHTOMO]
That's bizarre.
I put jamming cancelers
in all of them.
It should have worked.
This is exactly why I hate
getting involved with
that masked bastard.
How'd you do it?
Those poor people.
You used some weird power again
to brainwash them, right?
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Some weird power?"
Heh. It's simply
a gift I gave them.
Nothing more or less.
[grunts]
[AKECHI]
What did you tell them?
[TWENTY-FACES] I said
"You are the ones who will
protect this place. If the
security robots shut down,
you are to fight off
any intruders, no-- "
What are you guys talking about?
This is stupid.
[TWENTY-FACES] I hope the
police don't try to waltz in
to my new playground. If they
happen to bump into each other--
[YOSHIO]
Let's take Hanasaki and go!
[TWENTY-FACES] I wonder what
will happen. Hm, hm, hm.
Don't ignore me!
[AKECHI] Kobayashi! Be quiet
for a minute, would you?
[YOSHIO gasps]
Now I could stop them,
of course. It's not too late.
However.
I'll need something
from you. Kill him.
[gasps]
Do that, and I'll call
them off immediately.
Yeah, right.
Sacrificing just one life will
prevent the loss of dozens.
If you ask me, that's a bargain.
That's not happening.
You might as well.
The Hanasaki you knew
is long gone, my dear.
[AKECHI gasps]
[AKECHI]
Bastard. You got to him, too?
Which one would be more
thrilling for you?
That I got to him, or not?
I think we both know the answer.
[AKECHI gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Poor thing.
Can you continue to love him,
as you did before?
Stop talking.
Now. What's your answer?
That's enough!
Pull the trigger.
All of this... is my fault.
Do it. Kill me now!
[AKECHI gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Please, boss!
I deserve to die!
I can't let... you suffer.
Come on! Do it!
[KENSUKE grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES] Oh, and...
We can't forget your father.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[KENSUKE gasps]
Remember Isuzu, the woman
Haruhiko adored so much?
Your father sure does.
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki! Don't listen!
[TWENTY-FACES] Whether because
he was threatened,
or simply loved his adopted son.
Daddy dearest sent Ms. Isuzu
huge amounts of money
so your wayward brother would
be supported. Isn't that sweet?
[KENSUKE]
You're lying!
Perhaps he did it simply out
of concern for his company,
or because he truly cares
about Haruhiko's well-being.
[KENSUKE sobs]
You don't know how
your father feels.
[AKECHI]
Faces!
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
Yet you did this.
[AKECHI]
Damn you.
[KENSUKE sobs]
No more.
I've had enough. I did it.
It's all my fault.
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki!
[KENSUKE] Please, just kill me.
I want to die so badly.
That's my line.
Don't start copying me.
[KENSUKE gasps]
Understand?
Don't you dare. I'm the one
who's supposed to die. Not you!
[exhales]
[grunts]
There it is. Very nice.
I waited all this time for you
to grow fond of these boys.
Now, after finally getting to
see that look on your face.
I can say it was worth it.
[TWENTY-FACES] Things are
about to get interesting.
[YOSHIO]
Hey, old man. Shut up!
[YOSHIO] What's the plan?
Tell me what to do! Please!
Come on, why are just
you standing there?
[KENSUKE]
Just give it up.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[gasps]
Hansaki, no!
[KENSUKE] Don't do anything,
Kobayashi. Stay put.
[grunts]
I'll end it. It's the
only way I can atone.
[laughs]
You guys.
I'm sorry.
[AKECHI grunts]
[grunts]
Hanasaki!
[gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Wow.
Hm.
[chuckles]
[KENSUKE pants]
[gasps]
[INOUE gasps]
I guess it's over.
[INOUE]
Hm Fine by me.
[KENSUKE groans]
Kobayashi.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Too bad.
[AKECHI]
That's... enough.
[AKECHI grunts]
Let's just... end... it.
[TWENTY-FACES]
It won't end.
I love you too much for that.
[TWENTY-FACES] That's also
why I won't forgive you.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Thrilling, isn't it?
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[TWENTY-FACES]
That gift of yours.
It's far greater than mine.
[YOSHIO]
Gift? Tsk.
[TWENTY-FACES]
I'm a bit... jealous.
[police sirens]
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[TWENTY-FACES]
Let's play again soon.
[YOSHIO sighs]
Tsk.
[AKECHI grunts]
[NAKAMURA]
Wakey, wakey.
[AKECHI] Hey, Nao.
Can you give me a light?
[NAKAMURA]
You did good.
[AKECHI grunts]
With Twenty-Faces, I mean.
[AKECHI gasps]
[MIYANISHI] He should be
watched around the clock.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Thank goodness.
With him gone, we can
finally clean up his messes.
Of course, I'll be expecting
your assistance with that.
[KENSUKE gasps]
Remain on stand-by, for now.
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi!
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE]
About all that.
[YOSHIO] Whatever, just...
keep your promise.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
I'm waiting. Find a
way to kill me soon.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE sobs]
[KENSUKE]
Forgive me.
I'm so sorry. I am.
[yawns]
♪
[TWENTY-FACES] "Wild Dance
of the Luminous Man."