Hanasaki!
I'm sorry, Kobayashi.
I couldn't keep
my promise after all.
[INOUE]
Hanasaki!
Are you there?
Answer me!
[KENSUKE]
I'm here.
Don't know how, but I'm here.
[INOUE]
You're insane.
[GROUP sighs]
He'll be the death of me.
[KENSUKE]
We have to win this.
That's all that matters.
[KENSUKE]
It isn't sundown yet.
We can still save Akechi.
Sundown?
That was the time limit
Twenty-Faces gave us.
Unless we get the boss back by
then, he said he'd be changed.
He's clever.
Giving you that timeframe
made it impossible to get help
from the police.
It would've been over
by the time they mobilized.
[KENSUKE]
I'm ending this crap now.
I'll beat him once and for all.
No matter what it--
[NORO]
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold it!
That kinda talk's a death flag.
It's strictly forbidden.
[KENSUKE laughs]
Fair enough.
[INOUE]
Get serious!
[KENSUKE laughs]
Sorry.
But you know...
If I go in
expecting the worst,
maybe I'll pull a miracle.
You never know.
[INOUE]
Hanasaki.
You don't have to.
[KENSUKE]
Goin' in.
Later!
[INOUE]
Hanasaki!
No shock there.
It's not the time.
[YOSHIO]
Send me, too.
[NORO gasps]
Koba?
Get me up there! Now!
[KATSUTA]
Kobayashi.
[YAMANE]
It's too late.
He's already inside.
[YOSHIO]
I know that!
That's why you need to hurry!
Ohtomo, find a way to send him.
Huh? Why should I do it?
Afraid you can't?
[YOKOYANAGI]
Hey! Got a second?
Move it. Unless you'd
rather talk to the police.
[YOKOYANAGI] I have a
few questions for you.
Come with me, please.
And don't worry
about the plane.
We're forming a search
party as we speak.
[OHTOMO]
Think I'll pass.
Let's go, Yamane.
Hold on! Come back!
[INOUE]
I'll answer your questions.
Ask away.
I know everything
that you need to.
All about this case,
about Twenty-Faces,
and Detective Akechi Kogorou.
[OHTOMO]
He's so damn bossy.
[YAMANE]
Huh?
[OHTOMO] He could've just said
"Ohtomo, you're my only hope!"
[chuckles]
But then he might've
died of embarrassment.
Guess so. Heh.
You're not going
with them? Why not?
I'm not letting you
take this on by yourself.
[NORO] This might not
be the best time, but...
I wanted you to
know I'm grateful.
To have you with us, I mean.
[engine running]
[OHTOMO]
Thanks for waiting!
Slow down!
I can't do this if it slips out!
[OHTOMO]
Huh?
[NORO] That won't fly!
It's battery's dead!
[OHTOMO]
Yeah, yeah.
[YAMANE] Don't worry, I'm
giving it a speed charge now.
[YOSHIO]
Do it.
We've wasted enough time.
[OHTOMO] You should seriously
consider changing your name
to the Slave Drivers Club.
[NORO]
Pay attention, Koba.
With this level of charge, the
shuttle's only going to get you
as far as the plane's
landing system.
[YOSHIO]
I know. Let's go.
[OHTOMO]
Okay, okay.
But first, let's
go over the plan.
The shuttle accelerates on fuel,
so the battery won't
drain during launch.
Once you're past
the launch ramp,
activate the guidance system
on the control panel.
From there, the shuttle
will land itself on.
[YOSHIO] I told you
I got it, all right?
Just hurry and
get me to Hanasaki.
But...
[OHTOMO] Save your breath;
he'll be fine.
It's not like he can die.
[OHTOMO]
When you see him...
Tell him to come
by my lab again soon.
Made some new tech.
He can tell me
how awesome it is.
[YOSHIO]
Tell him yourself.
[OHTOMO]
Heh.
I'll do that.
[NORO]
Ready, Koba?
[YOSHIO]
You think?
[NORO]
All right, then.
You're off!
[OHTOMO]
Bon voyage!
[YAMANE]
Oh, no.
[OHTOMO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
Akechi?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Why are you here?
Why the hell do you think?
To win this! To save you!
Dumbass!
Leave it! Forget me!
[KENSUKE]
You're okay with losing to him?
[AKECHI]
Doesn't matter.
[KENSUKE]
It does!
I'll win and end this for good!
It's what we've all
been fighting for.
Right?
If not, then what's the point?
[TWENTY-FACES]
My, my.
You truly are resourceful.
I'm impressed.
But you're too late.
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[AKECHI]
Don't.
Why not?
He deserves it!
You've done enough.
I'm proud of you, kid.
Good job.
[AKECHI]
Truth be told,
all I wanted was to
look cool to you kids.
To be the hero in
my own little tragedy.
[KENSUKE]
Boss... What are you--
[AKECHI]
So do me a favor.
Let me look cool here.
[TWENTY-FACES]
How naughty.
You turned the helium system
up as high as it would go,
didn't you, Akechi?
[TWENTY-FACES] The change
in pressure and altitude
will tear the ship apart.
Only a matter of time.
Were you hoping we would
die in each other's arms?
[AKECHI]
Sorry, Hanasaki.
You're only in this
mess 'cause of me.
Just like the others.
I wanted them to see me.
To love me like I couldn't.
What are you
talking about, boss?
Just leave. I'll end this.
I should have a long time ago.
[TWENTY-FACES]
You should listen to him.
Escape while you can.
This plane will
fly apart any moment.
Besides, Akechi's finally
decided to play with me,
and three's a crowd.
Your role in all
of this is over.
[KENSUKE]
Shut up!
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki!
Get going!
Leave him to me. Please!
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki!
What a stubborn
little toy you found.
You've grown tired of him, yet
he refuses to leave your side.
Unacceptable.
[AKECHI]
No! Stop!
[gunshot]
Akechi!
[AKECHI groaning]
[KENSUKE]
It won't work.
You can't bring
yourself to kill him.
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki.
[KENSUKE] If you could,
this would all be over by now.
But you always run away
and let him escape.
Happens every time.
You're just too nice, Akechi.
That's a fact.
[KENSUKE]
Boss.
Sorry.
[AKECHI grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES]
You.
You really are like him,
aren't you, boy?
A colossal fool!
I worked so hard
to set this up for him.
He was ready to
sacrifice himself.
Akechi was finally ready.
We would have our
last thrill together!
[YOSHIO]
Hanasaki!
Koba, why?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Idiot.
You're such an idiot!
[YOSHIO]
You're supposed to kill me.
Did you forget?
You promised and
I'm holding you to it!
So don't ever leave me again!
[KENSUKE, YOSHIO yell]
[KENSUKE groans]
[YOSHIO]
Get off me, old man!
[TWENTY-FACES]
There are two rescue pods left,
and one of them is mine.
I'm going after Akechi
and continuing our game.
Don't try to follow.
The two of you are
inadequate at being playmates.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Kobayashi.
I truly pity you.
You don't even have the strength
to control your own gift.
Put the gun down
and let me leave.
Once I'm safely away, you two
can live or die as you please.
[YOSHIO]
Shoot him, Hanasaki!
Weren't you going
to end this crap?
Do it!
Stop worrying about me!
Right now, you just do
what you wanna do!
[YOSHIO] Once he's dead
and gone, it'll be over!
Then you can focus on
keeping your promise!
Pull the damn trigger!
I'm not gonna die here!
Kobayashi!
Get outta my way!
Kobayashi.
Where are you?
♪
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi!
Hang in there.
I'll get to you!
♪
Koba! Incoming!
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi, I'm sorry.
I just couldn't kill you.
At least this way...
...we'll die together.
[YOSHIO]
I see.
I was right all along.
I can die with you.
Hanasaki, thank you
for everything.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[AKECHI]
They'll be fine without me.
[AKECHI] When kids start
to think for themselves,
things tend to work out
for 'em in the long run.
It was the same with us.
Thanks, by the way.
For keeping your
promise all these years.
The thrills. You always
managed to surprise me.
I won't run away anymore.
Come on.
You can make a better
face than that, can't you?
You got twenty of 'em.
[laughing]
[TWENTY-FACES, AKECHI
laughing]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Akechi.
Isn't this fun?
[MALE TEACHER 24A]
Representative of graduates.
Your address.
Thank you, sir.
Spring is the season
of life renewed.
As the cold of the past is
replaced with the warmth
of the future,
we, the graduating class,
take our first steps
into those new lives,
guided by wisdom and hope.
[YUMEKO]
Um... 'Scuse me!
Sorry, but... um...
Could I have the
second button, please?
[INOUE]
All right.
I'll be sure to
ask Katsuta for you.
[YUMEKO]
Uh... oh.
Congratulations!
I hope you have a
wonderful life, Inoue.
Same to you.
[phone ringing]
[INOUE]
Akechi Investigation Firm.
[KENSUKE] Just calling to let
you know the lost child case
is in the bag.
[INOUE]
Good work.
[KENSUKE] We just dropped
him off at his house,
safe and sound.
[INOUE]
Good.
Welp, we're heading off
to the next one, bossman.
Wish us luck!
[INOUE]
Don't call me weird names.
[KENSUKE laughs]
All right, Koba.
Let's do this.
Sorry for the wait.
Not at all.
[KENSUKE whistling]
[INOUE] I appreciate all
the help you've given us.
But we still don't know
where Akechi ended up.
[NORO chuckles]
[YOKOYANAGI] True, but thanks
to your help and the data
Miyanishi left behind,
we were able to prove
Akechi wasn't Twenty-Faces.
His name is cleared.
That's a win.
Hey, could I ask
you for something?
This case I'm on.
I've kinda hit a snag.
If you're willing, I think...
...you'd be perfect for the job.
[KENSUKE whistling]
[KENSUKE]
Still got your power.
Guess at this point
you're stuck with it.
[YOSHIO]
Yeah.
[KENSUKE]
That okay with you?
[YOSHIO]
I don't have a choice.
It's part of me.
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[gasps]
[YOSHIO]
What the matter?
[KENSUKE]
That!
On the rooftop!
[YOSHIO] If you wanna die,
just do it already.
[KENSUKE]
Hey, lighten up.
You shouldn't encourage
this sorta thing.
[YOSHIO]
Really?
That's all you ever did for me.
[KENSUKE]
So, uh...
Hi there!
I dunno what's going on
with you, but we could help.
[TEEN BOY 24A]
The Boy Detectives' Club?
[KENSUKE laughs]
Well?
What'll it be?
You gonna die?
Or try to live?