[grunts]
[grunts, sighs]
[gasps]
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Hold up! He's okay!
Wait, Kobayashi!
[YOSHIO grunts]
It's fine, he's not inured! See?
Good thing you just
hit his right leg.
Calm down.
Nothing's screwed here, alright?
--[YOSHIO grunts]
--[KENSUKE gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
Whoa! What the hell
are you doing?
I'd ask you the same!
[YOSHIO sighs]
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
♪
[INOUE] It varies from job
to job, but the average fee is
One hundred-thousand yen per
three hours of investigation.
The startup fee will be
around fifty-five percent
of the estimated total fee.
If the job is completed,
you'll be billed for
the remaining total.
If it isn't completed,
the startup fee,
minus expenses,
will be refunded.
[MEIKO]
Uh. Sorry, but...
Is something wrong?
[MEIKO grunts]
Is Akechi here?
I'm afraid he's investigating
another matter.
--[AKECHI] Ah!
--[music playing]
The path I follow to
love is a mad dash!
Mad dash! Mad dash!
But safety should
always come first!
[FEMALE GAME VOICE]
Excellent!
[KENSUKE]
Eh, forget about him.
[MEIKO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE] If you hire the
Boy Detectives' Club
to take care of it,
you'll only pay half the cost!
[MEIKO] But, aren't you
busy with school?
[KENSUKE]
I'm home-schooled.
And the kid behind the
bird is a total shut-in.
[NORO]
Hey! Watch it!
[INOUE]
My high school is credits-based,
so I don't start until
third period today.
I appreciate
your concern, though.
[MEIKO]
Hm. Right.
Whaddya think?
I mean, if she really wants
the boss, we can talk to him.
Either way, we'll do
all the work.
[INOUE]
Hanasaki!
[MEIKO gasps]
[MEIKO]
Please!
Whoa! These look tasty!
[NORO gasps]
She brought treats?
You better not hog
them all to yourself!
[INOUE] So then, what exactly
would you like us to do?
Did you lose something?
Boyfriend cheating on ya?
Or do you need
your place cleaned?
[INOUE gasps]
Quite the collection.
Focus.
Leave everything to us.
We'll find the
culprit in no ti--
Actually, I already
know who made them.
[KENSUKE]
Oh. In that case,
we'll catch'em and
call it a day.
[MEIKO]
No, please.
My boyfriend who lives
with me; He made them.
[INOUE]
Ah.
[MEIKO] Lately, he's been
sneaking out at night
and doing something in secret.
I've been wondering what it was,
but then, I found
these in his desk.
If he just likes making stuff
like this, that's fine.
Then again...
[NORO] If it's more than that,
he could be major trouble.
[INOUE] Ah. Then what
you'd like from us is proof
that these letters are
meant for someone specific.
And whether or not any
have actually been
delivered to them, right?
Just some run-of-the-mill
gumshoe work.
[KENSUKE]
But that stuff's so boring.
Hanasaki...
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Hm...
[NAOKI] I'm workin' till
close today, alright?
[MEIKO]
Okay. Have a good one.
[NAOKI]
Hm.
[MEIKO]
[KENSUKE]
Hm.
[PIPPO hoots]
[car honks]
[INOUE]
Report.
[KENSUKE] The big seller's
the daily special,
but the others look good too.
'Specially the Hamburg Chicken.
[INOUE] Focus. My lunch
break's almost over.
[sighs]
[INOUE]
Is he social?
He's getting along
with his co-workers.
Even the Head Chef, who acts
like a total prick. Seems fine.
[INOUE]
Nothing suspicious about him?
[KENSUKE]
Uh... I dunno, yet.
[INOUE]
What do you mean?
I won't know until I
talk to him in person.
If I look into his eyes, they'll
tell me what he's really like.
[INOUE] I think you're missing
the whole point of "tailing".
[KENSUKE]
It's fine! Chill!
With all the customers he gets,
he'll forget about
me in a nanosecond.
[NAOKI]
Welcome.
One Hamburg Chicken.
Seaweed on the rice, please.
Spicy cod on top.
[NAOKI]
Extra rice?
Double extra!
Comin' right up.
[INOUE] So? Did his
eyes tell you anything?
Doesn't seem like someone
who'd send threat letters.
[INOUE]
Then what does he look like?
I don't know, man.
If I had to pick a word,
I guess I'd say "pure"?
I'm never asking
your opinion again.
[NAOKI] Here you go!
Six-hundred forty yen, sir.
[KENSUKE]
Sure thing. Wait.
Uh, uh... Seriously?
[COOK A]
Hey, what's wrong?
I think this guy lost his
wallet or something.
Oh, no! That's just terrible.
I can cover it, if you like.
[KENSUKE]
No, I'm fine! Really.
[NORO]
Way to be inconspicuous.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[VENDING MACHINE] In sixty
seconds you could be eating!
It's healthy and delicious.
The fresh lunch machine!
In sixty seconds you
could be eating...!
[PIPPO hoots]
[NORO]
If you can't even tail a guy,
Pippo here must be
five-googolplex times
as smart as you.
You're ruthless.
I'm freaking starving here.
[NORO] Aw, and here I thought
you lived on adrenaline.
[KENSUKE]
Can it!
[NORO grunts]
[MALE GAME VOICE]
Nice!
Looks like you're not the
only one whose feeding center
is in need of major stimulation.
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
[NORO] This is your most recent
electronic transaction history.
Your thief must
be starving, too.
Why don't you go fetch it?
You're useless to us
right now, anyway.
[KENSUKE groans]
Roger that!
[VENDING MACHINE]
Please choose a menu item.
You've chosen Tempura Udon.
Please choose the kind of
Tempura you would like.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[AKECHI] Heard your wallet
was stolen. What a loser.
[KENSUKE]
"Stolen" is a strong word.
Lemme guess, that weird kid?
[KENSUKE]
I think so.
[AKECHI] I see. And you're
sticking your nose into
his business again because
you want to help him?
[KENSUKE]
Every time he opens his mouth,
it's to say he wants to die.
But that'd be a total waste
of his awesome power!
[AKECHI] I don't know if this
kid actually wants your help
or not, Kensuke.
Don't get full of yourself.
[KENSUKE]
Uh...
It takes more than sound
reasoning to save someone.
[KENSUKE sighs]
Right!
[AKECHI sniffs]
Something smells.
[exhales]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE laughs]
What an idiot!
You really crack me up.
Who eats noodles
with their bare hands?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Ten, ten, and ten!
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
[KENSUKE]
Don't eat that. It's filthy!
[YOSHIO]
Now who's the idiot?
[laughs]
All right. It's time
for your first job!
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE] The Boy Detective's
Club just got a commission.
[YOSHIO]
No thanks.
[KENSUKE]
What? Why?
[YOSHIO]
You're annoying.
[KENSUKE] What's the problem?
I promised to kill you one day.
C'mon, join me!
Boy De-tec-tives Club!
[YOSHIO]
Go away.
[NORO]
He's moving!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[NORO] Looks like the target's
going on a pretty big
catering run. And from
the sound of it,
he practically begged the senior
chef into letting him do it.
'Kay, I'm on it. Just let
me know where he ends up.
Up and at 'em. Gonna need
your help tailing this guy.
Huh?
I almost lost him earlier thanks
to you snatching my wallet.
Time to work for that Udon.
[gasps]
I-I didn't...
[KENSUKE] I'll get you
something to eat later.
And, if I can,
I'll kill you too.
[YOSHIO]
I wasn't trying to steal it.
[KENSUKE]
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I figured you were trying to
bring it back to me. Let's go!
[YOSHIO grunts]
Today's the day. Hmph.
[NAOKI] Hi, I'm from Fuufuutei,
the catering service.
Is it cool if I
prepare the soup here?
[DOORMAN]
Sure.
There should already be
a room set up for you.
[NAOKI]
Thanks a lot.
[KENSUKE] So, how long have you
been squatting back there?
[YOSHIO]
Don't remember.
[KENSUKE]
When'd you get your power?
[YOSHIO]
I don't know!
[KENSUKE]
Where's your family?
I don't know.
Is there anything
you do remember?
[YOSHIO]
I don't know.
[KENSUKE]
You can't be worn out already.
[AKECHI]
Hey, guys.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[AKECHI] These threat letters.
They smell funny.
[NORO]
Uh! Funny how?
[AKECHI] What do you mean "how"?
They just smell.
It's almost like...
...they were dipped
in cheap cooking oil.
[NORO]
Huh?
Wait, you're saying
they smell, literally?
[AKECHI]
What else would I mean?
I thought you were just
trying to be dramatic.
[NORO] Wouldn't they
smell like cooking oil
because the target
works in a bento shop?
Oh! Now that you mention it,
there were flyers
taped up everywhere.
[AKECHI]
That's strange.
[NORO, KENSUKE]
Huh?
You make these things
to stay anonymous.
The whole point is not
to leave any clues.
But these are covered in them.
You got a point.
[AKECHI]
Also...
Our client's obviously an
organic-eating health nut.
Why would she go out with a guy
who works at a cheap bento shop?
Huh. I'll let you figure that
out while I stop this guy.
[VENDING MACHINE] In sixty
seconds you could be eating!
[KENSUKE] I said I'd
get you food later.
Come on.
Hold it. Now why are you
eating if you want to die?
[YOSHIO]
I have to eat.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
If I don't,
this power shoves anything
it can find down my throat.
[YOSHIO groans]
[KENSUKE gags]
Will you please let
me eat something?
[KENSUKE]
Soon, okay?
When we're done with this job,
I'll get you anything you want.
Deal?
Anything I want?
[gulps]
[KENSUKE]
We'll split up here.
[FRONT DESK MAN] Hey! You kids
can't just walk in here!
[KENSUKE] Oh. I have business
with someone inside, sir.
[FRONT DESK MAN]
Yeah? Who's that?
I'll call 'em
down here for you.
[KENSUKE] Actually, I would
prefer that they not know
I'm here just yet.
[FRONT DESK MAN gasps]
[KENSUKE] Look, man.
I'm kind of in a hurry here.
[FRONT DESK MAN]
Aren't you a student?
Uh...
[INOUE] He's from the NTU
High School newspaper club.
I apologize for his
lack of manners, sir.
He heard he was interviewing
Dr. Senou, one of our alumni,
and he got a
little over excited.
The fool left an hour ahead of
schedule without telling me.
[FRONT DESK MAN]
I see.
[INOUE] I realize it's still
in front of the venue,
but if it wouldn't
be too much trouble,
I'd greatly appreciate it
if you would allow him to
wait in the lobby with me.
[KENSUKE]
Nice going!
[grunts]
Huh?
[YOSHIO sniffs]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[EVENT ORGANIZERS chatter]
The catered meal is
ready and waiting, sir.
I'll be back in bit,
Doctor Senou.
[MEIKO]
Isn't Dr. Senou on TV a lot?
[INOUE]
Yes. He's quite famous.
Do you know if Naoki has
anything against his ideology?
Or research?
[MEIKO] He did yell at the TV
a lot whenever he was on.
Something about violating
the laws of nature.
[INOUE]
I see.
[MEIKO] I'm sorry,
I need to get back to work.
[NORO]
Hm... Pretty crazy.
[MEIKO]
Um. He'll be okay, right?
[INOUE]
I'll call when we're done.
[gasps]
Wait, wasn't that?
[YOSHIO blows]
How much food are you
planning to steal?
[YOSHIO gasps]
I'm not stealing.
[KENSUKE]
Dude, I just saw you.
Well. What choice do I have--
[grunts]
[gasps]
Hey!
[YOSHIO chokes]
[coughs]
Whoa, are you dying?
[YOSHIO]
The soup!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[YOSHIO]
Something in there is deadly.
[KENSUKE]
What?
[YOSHIO] The same thing
happened when I drank gasoline.
For real?
[NAOKI]
What are you doing?
[YOSHIO, KENSUKE gasp]
This food is for the conference.
It was. Dinner is cancelled
as of this moment.
Sorry, pal. No one is getting
near these death dishes!
Idiot!
[NAOKI]
Hold on. It's you!
Fess up. We know you
poisoned the food.
Don't try denying it.
I didn't poison it!
[KENSUKE] We also know
you begged your senior chef
for this job. The jig's up.
Because, I--
I also looked over
the catering menu
and couldn't find
soup anywhere on it.
I- I just wanted to...
...to show everyone how
amazing this water is.
Huh?
[NAOKI] I recommended
it to the guys at work,
but none of them would listen.
Then, I thought if a
bigshot doctor gave it his
seal of approval, people might
finally see how good it is.
[KENSUKE]
Seriously?
Yeah, bro.
This stuff is the best!
It clears your body
of all kinds of junk
and makes food
taste even better.
[KENSUKE]
O-Okay, wait a sec.
I'm having trouble
following all this.
[NAOKI] Now, what did
you mean by "poison"?
I just wanted these people to
get a taste of my cooking!
Honest!
So, you really don't know
anything about this, huh?
Kobayashi!
[YOSHIO grunts]
What? I didn't do anything!
[KENSUKE]
Let's go!
[YOSHIO]
Okay.
Hanasaki!
[KENSUKE]
I heard it!
On the phone earlier,
I heard the same sound
when Kobayashi broke
the vending machine!
That chick's gotta be
somewhere in the area!
[NORO]
Inoue, look at this.
Is Meiko the one who
came up with this plan?
What plan? I don't know what
you're talking about, dude!
So, should we take both of them
into custody? For now, at least?
[EVENT ORGANIZER A grunts]
[INOUE] The one who prepared
all this mineral water.
It was Meiko, right?
[gasps]
[INOUE]
The threat letters, as well.
She even poisoned the food.
And then, she tried to frame
you for the entire thing.
[NORO] What? So...
This guy was just being played?
No, you're wrong.
Stop lying about her!
Meiko would never do that.
I'd stake my life on it!
No, don't!
Ah. There, ya see?
I'm perfectly fine.
Meiko didn't--
[NAOKI gasps]
[NAOKI gurgles]
[EVENT ORGANIZER B gasps]
Call an ambulance!
[EVENT ORGANIZER B]
Right!
[grunts]
[YOSHIO]
I don't get it.
We caught the guy,
isn't that enough?
[KENSUKE]
Something still doesn't add up.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE] If that girl was
trying to frame her boyfriend,
why would she hang out near
the scene of the crime?
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
I've just got a bad feeling.
I'd rather be sure that
I'm wrong, than be right
and not do anything.
[exhales]
But I don't care.
I already ate my fill,
and then some.
Listen, you!
[grunts]
Ow! Dammit!
I don't have time
for this crap.
[gasps]
[INOUE]
Hanasaki, where are you?
[YOSHIO grunts]
[INOUE] Hey! Answer me!
Can you hear me, Hanasaki?
This again?
[DR. SENOU]
Through genetic design,
we can eliminate hereditary
illness altogether.
Thank you, miss.
My pleasure, sir.
[KENSUKE grunts]
Hey! Is anyone in there?
[YOSHIO]
Move.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[MEIKO chuckles]
[MEIKO, DR. SENOU gasp]
[KENSUKE chuckles]
You're the man!
Back to work.
Old timer!
Don't drink the water!
You'll die!
[EVENT ORGANIZER A]
Doctor! Are you alright?
[grunts]
[shouts, grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Sorry.
I got so pissed off that
I forgot to hold back.
[MEIKO gasps]
[KENSUKE] Your boyfriend's dead.
Hope you're happy.
[MEIKO]
I was just protecting myself!
[KENSUKE]
Enough!
[gasps]
[KENSUKE] We know you
came to us with that job
to make us suspect your
boyfriend from the start.
Then, when it looked
like he screwed up,
you came to finish the old
man by yourself. Right?
[MEIKO grunts, gasps]
[KENSUKE] Here're the
results of my investigation.
Your boyfriend was an honest,
stand-up guy.
One who worked really hard to
make his girlfriend happy.
And in the end, he was far too
good a man for a girl like you.
Thanks for choosing the
Boy Detective's Club.
[EVENT ORGANIZER A]
On your feet.
[EVENT ORGANIZER B]
Let's go.
[KENSUKE]
Hm? Something wrong?
[gasps] Nothing. It's just...
You, uh... dropped this.
[KENSUKE] Heh. I see.
Can't help admiring me, can you?
[YOSHIO]
Uh...
Look, if you wanted it,
you just had to ask me.
Want it? That's not...
You did great for your
first case! Ha, ha!
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[KENSUKE]
Let's work hard together!
[YOSHIO grunts]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[YOSHIO] If I'm with him...
maybe I'll finally...
Well?
[YOSHIO]
If you really insist.
I guess.
[AKECHI] The police still
can't get that girl to talk.
[KENSUKE]
I see.
[AKECHI sighs] Nao kept going
on about some group the girl
got sucked in to.
But I don't really get it.
[KENSUKE]
It doesn't matter now.
It won't bring
her boyfriend back.
That kid. Have you
made a decision?
[KENSUKE] I have. I've decided
I'm going to have a race.
[AKECHI]
Hm?
I'd like to see if I can either
find a way to kill him first,
or make him realize he wants
to stay among the living.
I guess you could say I'm
having a race with myself.
What's that look?
Soup's ready. Dig in.
Ha, ha. Right!
[radio music plays]
[YOSHIO breathes heavily]
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"The Hopeless on the Tower."