[KENSUKE]
Check this out, Haru!
I'm gonna make it back to the
house without falling off!
[HARUHIKO]
Cool.
[KENSUKE] Hey, why aren't
you watching me?
[HARUHIKO]
Sorry. This caught my eye.
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
[HARUHIKO]
A detective firm!
[KENSUKE]
What's that?
They're freelancers who help
people that are in need.
Haruhiko.
[HARUHIKO] You can put your
doubts to rest. We're family.
You won't lose me again.
♪
[NORO] The police tried getting
past those nasty turrets,
but had no luck.
Now they've got their hands
full keeping the press
and gawkers from
swarming the place.
I'd say it's a pretty safe
bet you boys aren't getting
anywhere near that fortress
without Nakamura's help.
Did you catch all that, Nao?
[NAKAMURA] Loud and clear.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
[AKECHI] Sorry we had
to interrupt your fun.
Can it. There's a
child listening, you jerk.
[AKECHI]
What's the situation?
[NAKAMURA] We got a call from
someone in the complex.
I'll let you know when
I find out what he said.
Also...
[NORO] They fired warning
shots at a press helicopter?
[NAKAMURA]
Exactly.
[AKECHI]
Well, that's not nice.
[NORO]
Check out the news footage.
It's pretty heavy stuff.
Any word from Hanasaki?
[NORO] No, but his
GPS is in the complex.
Of course it is.
[ANNOUNCER] Entering the yellow
zone is strictly forbidden
to any who are not
citizens of this borough.
[OLD MAN]
Soups on, Haru!
[HARUHIKO, KENSUKE gasp]
You'd better get down
here before it's all gone!
I thought things would work
themselves out if I left home.
Huh?
[HARUHIKO] I quickly
learned that was foolish.
My money ran out
before I knew it.
[HARUHIKO]
"Maybe I was wrong," I thought.
[HARUHIKO] But just as I
started to feel that way...
[HARUHIKO]
...Mom reached out and saved me.
[HARUHIKO] She convinced me
I'd made the right choice.
I owe her and this
family everything.
Even so...
[HARUHIKO exhales]
[KENSUKE] One mistake
and that helicopter--
[HARUHIKO] Hey, I don't
like it any more than you.
But, it's the only way I know
to keep this family safe.
[KENSUKE] It won't for long.
They'll find a way around it.
[HARUHIKO]
It'll be fine!
[KENSUKE gasps]
If we conduct ourselves
properly, someone is bound
to see that we're right
and reach out to us.
[gasps]
[MIYANISHI]
Where the hell are you?
[NAKAMURA]
I'm on scene. Where else?
[MIYANISHI gasps] You're acting
on your own? Are you crazy?
Think of it as making
up for lost time.
[MIYANISHI]
Fine. Not like I can stop you.
[DETECTIVE] Their representative
is on the line again!
We'll take it here.
[NAKAMURA]
Merge the calls.
[MIYANISHI]
Yeah, keep your shirt on.
[ISUZU]
Have you done as I asked?
[BOSS B] You know we haven't.
We need more time.
[ISUZU chuckles]
Come now.
Three billion shouldn't
be hard to get.
So, all they want is money?
You're insane.
[ISUZU]
Alright, I'll sweeten the deal.
What if we let the police
take all the credit?
I don't follow.
[ISUZU] Pay us and we'll
pretend to be terrorists
instead of citizens.
We get rich,
and you become heroes
in the eyes of the public.
Make your choice quickly.
[TWENTY-FACES] All done
pretending to be a savior?
[ISUZU]
Hm?
I see you made good
use of my presents.
Were they what you hoped for?
[ISUZU] They were! I can't thank
you enough for all your--
And where's his?
[ISUZU gasps]
[TWENTY-FACES]
Haruhiko's passport?
[ISUZU]
Hm.
[TWENTY-FACES] You certainly
have him and the others fooled,
don't you? Your selfless
conviction and your precious
family were nothing more than
tools to make a fortune.
[ISUZU]
Are you angry with me?
Angry? No, I expected this.
[ISUZU gasps]
Now, let's raise
the curtain, shall we?
[ANNOUNCER] Entering the yellow
zone is strictly forbidden
to any who are not citizens...
So, what is all this?
An anti-personnel radar.
They just attack anyone
who enters, no matter who it is?
Yeah, that's the general idea.
How's it lookin, Noro?
Not good. Their power
is isolated.
I can't hack into it.
Then our plan's laid out for us.
We'll find and shut
down their generator.
Once their security
system is offline,
the residents will
have to submit.
[NORO] The moment you
get close, they'll waste you.
I don't think that'll be
a problem. Right, kid?
I can't talk you
out of this, boss?
Only if you got a better plan.
I don't. But is he reliable?
He's your teammate.
Have a little more faith.
Hey, Kobayashi.
Huh?
Question. You still wanna die?
This is messed up!
You can't go along with this!
[HARUHIKO]
Messed up? How?
[KENSUKE] I don't know. I just
don't like it! Any of it!
This place, that old lady...
Did he put some foolish
idea in your head?
Huh?
[HARUHIKO]
Akechi Kogorou.
Wait. How do you know--
[car horn blares]
[POLICEMAN]
Hey! Knock it off!
Didn't you see the news, sir?
This road's off limits.
I'm sorry. I know you
were enjoying your date.
You have no idea, pal.
I'll need you to take
another route, sir.
[YOSHIO] I just have to
get inside the wall, right?
I'll give you instructions
after that.
Don't turn your phone off.
[YOSHIO]
Mm.
They'll fire five seconds
after the warning.
Make sure you're inside by--
I know. I'm not deaf.
Hey!
[ANNOUNCER]
Entering the yellow zone...
You might wanna move!
Tsk.
[AKECHI]
Five, four, three, two...
[explosion]
What the hell was that?
[POLICEMAN B]
Report!
[NAKAMURA]
Hm.
[HARUHIKO]
What's the commotion?
[RESIDENT A]
Checking now!
I'm heading your way.
Hold it!
[HARUHIKO]
Hm?
My boss. How do you
know about him?
[HARUHIKO grunts]
[alarms blarring]
[ANNOUNCER] This is a warning.
Repeat: This is a warning.
You have passed the
wall into the red zone.
Turn back now...
Pretty pathetic wall.
[ANNOUNCER]
This is your last chance.
Gunfire will commence
in ten seconds.
Ten...
Huh?
[RESIDENT C]
Get out of here!
[AKECHI]
Ignore them.
I was planning on it.
Do you wanna die?
Don't test us, kid.
We will shoot!
[ANNOUNCER]
One...
[RESIDENTS gasp]
[RESIDENTS whisper]
[AKECHI] Hey, you. Where's this
little nation's power plant?
Vigilante corps, arm yourselves
and meet at Building F.
Everyone else, stay indoors
and wait for instructions.
[KENSUKE]
Hey!
[HARUHIKO]
That means you, too!
[KENSUKE]
Wait up, would ya?
You're being a pest, Kensuke.
Listen.
[HARUHIKO sighs]
After I left home,
your "boss" came to see me.
[KENSUKE gasps]
It was right after I came here.
You're Haruhiko Hanasaki, right?
Your brother's lookin' for you.
I'm sorry.
There's nobody here
by that name, sir.
This young man is my son.
That's right.
I see. Then stay
out of his life.
What?
Unless you cut ties
with that shady hag,
I don't want you anywhere
near him, you got that?
Who the hell do
you think you are?
I won't say it again.
Don't let him see how pathetic
you've become. Understand?
[HARUHIKO]
Uh...
What?
[HARUHIKO]
I repeat; Vigilante Corps,
I need you to assemble
at Building F!
[KENSUKE]
Wait. Are you saying that--?
[HARUHIKO]
Hey! You three!
[AKECHI]
This is the place.
[YOSHIO]
'Kay.
We need your help, too!
There's an intruder inside the--
[RESIDENT C] Help you?
Screw that!
[HARUHIKO]
Huh?
[OLD MAN] You told us this place
would be safe, no matter what!
[RESIDENT B] That's the only
reason we came here. You liar!
[HARUHIKO gasps]
[KENSUKE] Come on, bro.
We should leave too.
This is a time when family
should come together!
[RESIDENT B]
Enough with the family crap!
[HARUHIKO] Please!
You have to listen to--
[explosion]
Good work, kid.
[RESIDENTS shouting]
It's over, don't you see?
I need to find mother.
Listen to me!
I have to save her.
She won't stop fighting,
even if it gets her killed.
[AKECHI]
Sure about that?
[gasps]
Why are you here?
It's too bad, hag.
You were so close to
making your fortune.
What are you babbling on about?
[AKECHI] Don't resist and
I don't have to shoot you.
[HARUHIKO]
Did you plan this, Kensuke?
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
You finding me here.
Was it all a big lie?
N-No. Of course not!
I thought we were family.
Brothers.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[groans]
Haru!
His gun! Pick it up!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[AKECHI]
Hanasaki!
Why are you doing this, boss?!
[AKECHI sighs] Forget it.
Just don't move.
[KENSUKE]
Answer me!
[AKECHI]
Get out of the way, kid.
Please, I don't understand!
What the hell are
you doing, Haruhiko?
Shoot him! Quickly!
[AKECHI]
Don't bother.
There's nothing here that's
worth protecting anymore.
[HARUHIKO growls]
Bastards. This is
all because of you!
Drop it.
Haru, no!
Why are you just
standing there?
I had a feeling you
could handle the rest.
Talk to me! Brother!
[HARUHIKO]
Get... away.
Huh?
[HARUHIKO]
Don't... touch me.
[gasps]
[NEWSCASTER] The Kokorogaoka
Housing Complex independence
attempt that started with
a hijacked broadcast,
has ended in just half a day
after a daring police raid.
[INOUE]
Do you think Hansaki is okay?
[AKECHI]
Hm? Don't worry, he's fine.
Just getting a lecture.
[INOUE]
That isn't what I meant.
[AKECHI]
Huh?
[INOUE] He finally found
his brother. And now...
[YOSHIO]
Hey.
[gasps]
Can I go home now?
[INOUE]
You know you can't.
[YOSHIO yawns] I don't get why
I have to wait for him, too.
You were a contributor.
We couldn't have
done it without you.
[YOSHIO]
C-Contributor?
[AKECHI]
Inoue, google it for him.
[INOUE]
Not happening.
[AKECHI]
Hm?
[NAKAMURA]
You love making trouble for us.
[AKECHI]
Sorry about that.
[INOUE]
We're leaving.
Hanasaki?
[KENSUKE]
Apparently Twenty-Faces
was involved in all this.
[KENSUKE]
Nakamura told me.
[AKECHI] We don't know how
involved he was, though.
[KENSUKE] Haruhiko said they
had some kind of helper.
[AKECHI]
I see.
[MIYANISHI grunts]
At least you're safe.
Go home and rest, okay?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Why?
[MIYANISHI]
Eh?
[KENSUKE]
Why didn't you tell me anything?
[INOUE]
You left the office.
We didn't know about
Twenty-Faces until after that.
[KENSUKE]
I meant the boss.
[INOUE gasps]
You knew where Haru was.
Don't deny it.
None of this would've
happened if you'd told me!
I don't recall taking
your request.
Huh?
[AKECHI]
You were never a client to me.
Wha--?
[AKECHI]
That day, I never took the job,
so there was no reason for
me to tell you anything.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE growls]
You bastard!
[AKECHI]
Heh. You're wide open.
In many ways.
[KENSUKE grunts]
Shut up!
[gasps]
[MIYANISHI]
Akechi!
[AKECHI] You've never learned
to keep your emotions in check.
[KENSUKE gasps]
My brother.
My life... All of
it is your fault!
Casting blame, now?
Must be easy.
[growls]
[INOUE]
Enough! Both of you!
[NAKAMURA] You do realize you're
in police headquarters, right?
[AKECHI]
Nao, could you give him a lift?
[NAKAMURA]
Sure.
[AKECHI] Hanasaki, you're banned
from work for now. Go cool off.
[KENSUKE] Don't bother.
I won't work for you anymore.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Where are you-- Ugh, let's go.
[MIYANISHI]
M-Me, too?
[YOSHIO]
Are we done?
[INOUE grunts]
Let's go home, then.
[INOUE]
You are such a--
[AKECHI]
He's right. I need sleep.
We'll start early.
[INOUE]
Start what?
[AKECHI]
We've got jobs, don't we?
[KENSUKE]
Here's fine.
Hey, uh, is there
anything I can do?
[NAKAMURA]
Yeah. I didn't think so. Sorry.
You're angry, I get it,
but he's just looking out for--
[KENSUKE]
Bye.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh?
Whoa, no way. He's a rich kid?
You're kidding, right? I thought
you'd know more about them,
considering your
work relationship.
I don't wanna know.
Huh?
I can't. If I did, it'd be
too easy to get attached.
[AKASHI]
Welcome home.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE]
Where's Dad?
[AKASHI] He had some work
that required his attention.
[KENSUKE]
And Haru?
[AKASHI]
I don't know.
[KENSUKE scoffs] Like he hadn't
heard everything already.
[AKASHI] Could I get you
anything for dinner, sir?
I'll bring it to
your room, if you like.
Which hospital is he in?
I need to see him.
Please, Kensuke.
Come on! He's a
part of this family!
[AKASHI] The Hanasaki's have
no connection to that incident,
or any of the suspects involved.
[gasps]
[AKASHI] If the press should
come here asking questions,
please give them exactly
the same answer.
Is this you, or dad
talking right now?
[AKASHI] I took the liberty of
leaving fresh clothes on your--
But, what about Haru?
[AKASHI]
Please. Remain quiet.
Let this blow over
for a few days.
[AKASHI]
I beg you.
[AKASHI] If another tragedy
befalls the Hansaki family,
it will destroy us.
[KENSUKE exhales]
[seagulls chirp]
Inoue, how's it going?
He's arrived at the scene with
another woman. A third one.
[AKECHI] Damn. That hound.
He's good, I'll give him that.
[INOUE]
And you?
[AKECHI] Mm. We've almost got
everything cleaned up.
[gasps]
[AKECHI]
Okay, on to the next one.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[INOUE] You're very devoted
to your work, lately.
[AKECHI]
Huh? Yeah, well, staying busy
keeps other thoughts at bay.
[INOUE]
Hm?
For all of you.
[gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
[AKECHI]
Good work.
[YOSHIO] Dammit, I still
can't kill myself.
Jeez, what a crying shame.
[grunts]
[exhales]
--[phone rings]
--[KENSUKE gasps]
[FEMALE RECORDING] Sorry.
This customer is unavailable.
You may hang up, or leave
a message after the tone.
[beeps]
[NAKAMURA] It's me.
Thanks for the help earlier.
Kobayashi really
saved our hides.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NAKAMURA] I wasn't sure
about him when he first joined,
but now that my rep at
the station is back up,
I'm all for him!
I wanna talk about your
commission fee, so call me back.
Thanks again.
[KENSUKE growls]
[gasps]
[INOUE]
Hanasaki?
What's up?
You're still on probation.
What are you doing here?
[NORO]
Sheesh, lighten up, would you?
[KENSUKE] I just... came to
get my stuff, is all.
[YOSHIO]
Here.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Eat it.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
You're looking pretty pale.
You must be hungry.
[KENSUKE]
I'll pass.
Just take one.
[KENSUKE]
I don't want any!
Don't get all high-and-mighty
just cause they praised you!
[NORO]
Hey, chill, you jerk.
It's fine. I'm going to bed.
[NORO]
Good work today, Koba!
I thought you couldn't
stand him. What changed?
Stop acting like such a brat.
So it's like that now, is it?
I thought you'd be happy to
see him doing so well here.
Oh, I get it. How typical.
The hell are you
muttering about?
"Kobayashi's way more handy
than the adrenaline junkie."
Handy?
[NORO]
Quit taking this out on Koba!
[KENSUKE] Hm! C'mon.
We all know it's true.
He's practically invincible.
It's cool!
Hell, I felt the same.
But I really just kept
him around for laughs.
Hanasaki!
[KENSUKE] So don't get full
of yourself, you damn freak.
Think I care about you?
Well you're nothing to me!
[AKECHI]
You've crossed the line.
[gasps]
[AKECHI] Being a spoiled
rich kid doesn't mean
you can walk all over people.
Shut up!
Look, I get that you're in pain.
But if you think that gives
you the right to be cruel,
News flash, Kensuke.
You're dead wrong.
Shut up! Just shut
your damn mouth!
I hate every last one of you!
You're the bad guys here,
not me! Go to hell!
[INOUE]
Hanasaki!
[AKECHI grunts]
[yawns]
Bed time.
[INOUE gasps]
Nothing fazes you, does it?
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Don't you feel?
[KENSUKE pants]
[KENSUKE] Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it!
[KENSUKE pants]
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE whimpers]
[KENSUKE]
Screw that jerk.
Screw all of them!
[shouts]
[TWENTY-FACES]
That's right.
He's pure evil. I should know.
[KENSUKE sobs]
Let's chat.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Innocence Scale."