Ugh. Damn it!
Hey, look out!
[crashing noise]
Thought I was dead for sure.
[rumbling noise]
That doesn't sound good.
Now we've got you.
Pippo? You there?
Oh, good! You're all okay!
No, we're not okay!
We lost our ride!
[KENSUKE]
He got us again.
[YOSHIO]
Was it my fault?
Nah, it wasn't anyone's fault.
Well, Noro?
You got any other ideas?
[NORO]
Huh?
There has to be another way
to get up to the ship.
[NORO]
The shuttle was our only ticket!
[KENSUKE sighs]
[YOSHIO]
How 'bout that?
The one below us.
It flies.
Oh! Koba, I could kiss you.
[NORO]
That won't work!
Do you morons not know
how high the stratosphere is?
[KENSUKE]
There's still a chance, right?
[NORO]
Ugh! Practically zero!
That means we've got a shot.
[NORO]
This is a total waste of time!
Noro, you know
you can't stop him.
[NORO]
Ugh!
Tell ya what.
While we do this, you come
up with some super insane
backup plan.
As soon as you have it, we'll
switch gears. Sound good to you?
[NORO]
That's stupid!
You should regroup with Inoue
and come up with a new strategy.
Sorry, no can do.
Sounded like an explosion.
I hope Kensuke and
Koba are okay.
What's the plan?
Stay here and hold them
off as long as we can.
That's what I promised Hanasaki.
Take him down.
[INOUE gasps]
Capture them!
[SPECIAL SECURITY yelling]
[AKECHI grunts]
[TWENTY-FACES laughs]
I've had this thrill in
the works for a while now.
I hope you like it. Heh.
[KENSUKE yells]
[SECURITY ROBOT 23A]
Warning.
You are engaging
in unlawful activity.
Desist, or physical force
will be employed.
[KENSUKE]
Damn it!
[SECURITY ROBOT 23B]
Warning.
You are engaging
in unlawful activity.
D'you mean the shuttle?
We didn't blow it up,
you scrap heap!
[SECURITY ROBOTS]
Desist, or physical force...
[KENSUKE]
Dammit! Would you listen to me?!
[KENSUKE grunts]
Let him go!
[SPECIAL SECURITY 22E chuckles]
[SPECIAL SECURITY 22E yells]
[YAMANE]
Wow, Inoue!
What now?
We should find cover.
But what about your legs?
They're okay now.
You really are amazing, Inoue.
I hope you know that.
I can count on you.
I know that for sure.
[YAMANE]
Yeah!
How much longer?
Good question.
Three more games?
Who knows?
Maybe it's the last hurrah.
These rust buckets have
us totally pinned down.
Dammit, we don't have
time for this crap.
[YOSHIO]
You go on ahead.
I mean, look.
It's not like I'm gonna die.
Good point.
Here goes!
[SECURITY ROBOT 23A] You are
engaging in unlawful activity.
Put a sock in it!
[KENSUKE] Play with
that for a while, 'kay?
Damn, he's awesome.
Thanks, man!
Nice!
[INAGAKI chuckles] Don't have
the guts to shoot someone?
[crashing noise]
The hell? What's going on?
Is it an earthquake?
What? That's a Moon Excavator!
Is there someone driving it?
You really came to help us!
Thanks, Ohtomo!
Now I know why it's a prototype.
It shakes like
you wouldn't believe.
Quit gawking and shoot!
Back inside!
For real?
Those are nothing.
[INOUE]
Oh, no.
Get away! Quick!
Damn it!
He used sleeping gas.
Get your masks on!
Shooting those down
is top priority!
[OHTOMO] Akechi can
go to hell for all I care.
But I'd appreciate it if
you didn't bully my friends.
[KENSUKE groaning]
Damn it!
Come on!
Move, you piece of junk!
Ugh! I don't have
time for this!
[KENSUKE]
It's gonna work!
This way! Hurry!
Hold on, do you know
how to fly this thing?
Well, yeah. I mean, the actual
driving part is super easy.
They were designed for
ease of use in an emergency.
Hang tight, boss.
We're coming.
[SPECIAL SECURITY chattering]
[SPECIAL SECURITY yelling]
Yes! He's got'em cornered!
We might actually
pull this off, guys!
[INOUE]
What happened?
[OHTOMO sighs]
Well, it was fun
while it lasted.
All the vehicles on
display might be real,
but they only have enough power
to perform minor functions.
Why aren't we flying?
[INAGAKI] They were intended
to put on a little performance
for the public,
and yours just ended.
[AKECHI grunts]
[AKECHI grunting]
[AKECHI]
You.
[TWENTY-FACES]
Let's stop pretending, shall we?
You know why you're here.
[TWENTY-FACES] I've been
given an incredible gift.
Let's be honest.
It's a miracle,
and I couldn't be more
grateful for it, dear, Akechi.
[TWENTY-FACES] I wanted to
"pay it forward," as it were.
To give someone else
a gift that they, too,
would come to
see as a miracle.
I was a fool.
I couldn't see your words
for what they were:
The lies of a
self-deluding monster.
[AKECHI]
What do you mean?
[TWENTY-FACES] "You'll
get what you have coming.
It serves you right."
That is how you truly felt about
your father when you left him.
[TWENTY-FACES] All grown-ups
should be shields for the young.
Saviors.
Even at the cost
of their own life.
The real Akechi certainly
had that down pat.
Ah, you shut your mouth!
You killed both of your fathers.
You are a villain,
through and through.
All for thrills.
More thrills.
I was so moved by the
words you kept spouting,
I couldn't see it.
I focused on my desire
to give you constant thrills,
so you would be
happy for once.
Foolish.
I should have realized
you were numb
when it comes to
other's people's pain,
but I was blinded
by my own feelings.
[TWENTY-FACES] When someone
says "it's my fault,"
people tell them
that it isn't so.
If someone is repentant, others
are likely to forgive them.
Damn you!
I wonder...
Is that kindness
or self-interest?
Be quiet!
[TWENTY-FACES]
You're so pathetic.
Even now you're deluding
yourself by pretending
to care for those children.
[AKECHI]
What the hell do you know?
[growls]
Yet from the beginning,
you've told them they were
responsible for everything,
even their own deaths.
I'll let you in
on a secret, Akechi.
When people act
unnerved toward someone,
they're either faking it
or they've been presented
with irrefutable proof
that the other person
isn't what they seem.
When it comes to your crimes,
you've never felt any pride,
responsibility,
or even been aware of
them in the first place.
That you fight for justice
is irony incarnate.
[AKECHI]
You don't know me!
[TWENTY-FACES]
You are nothing more..
...than a complete fool.
[AKECHI grunts]
It's not my fault you suffer.
Come on, look at me.
[TWENTY-FACES]
What's wrong?
I'm right here.
[laughing]
What a spoiled boy you are.
Damn you!
[AKECHI grunts]
No need to throw
a tantrum, Akechi.
You should appreciate the pain.
Savor it.
After all...
That pain is the only
proof you're still alive.
[AKECHI]
Bastard.
Bastard!
I hope you burn in hell!
I'll send you there myself!
Do you hear me?
You damn monster!
I love this expression.
[INAGAKI] We know you're
in here somewhere, boys.
So listen.
This is your last chance
to submit peacefully.
If you don't...
[INOUE grunts]
Your friend will need
more than a wheelchair
by the time I'm done.
What kinda cops are you?
[SPECIAL SECURITY 23C]
Shut up!
[INAGAKI] We're what every
police officer should be.
Safety through the
preservation of order!
We're willing to do
whatever is needed
to achieve this end.
That's against everything
you stand for!
[INAGAKI] That's it!
That's the reaction!
Revolution will always be fought
by the morals of the past.
That's why those who bring about
change have to be charismatic
to the core!
But you don't have any charisma,
so you used Akechi as a
scapegoat and scared the public.
Yes.
Nothing is more unnerving
than finding out your hero
was actually a
villain all along.
The people will beg
for our protection.
Akechi's sacrifice will bring
about the peace and order
that this country
has only dreamed of.
[INOUE]
You're insane.
Detective Nakamura wanted this.
Was she insane, as well?
[INOUE]
Of course not!
She was controlled
by Twenty-Faces!
The enemy of
my enemy is my friend.
[KATSUTA]
You're sick.
My dream is to join the
police and protect people,
not rule over them with fear.
Really, now?
Well, that's a problem.
It's that kind of naïve,
moralistic thinking
that ruined the police.
It made us weak and docile.
Guess I'll have to
open your eyes.
[YAMANE]
Katsuta!
Idiot.
Come out!
Don't you care about them?
We'll kill--
[INOUE]
You're wasting your breath.
But by all means, keep it up.
Oh?
So you're saying there's
no need to keep you alive.
Thanks for clearing that up.
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KATSUTA]
Stop this!
Don't do it!
--[SECURITY ROBOT 23B] Unlawful.
--[INAGAKI] Subdue them!
[SECURITY ROBOT 23B]
Unlawful. Warning.
Hey, man, nice aerial attack.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
[laughs]
Thanks for distractin' em!
[SECURITY ROBOT 23B]
Warning. Warning. Cease.
Hanasaki!
By the way,
did it even occur to you
that we were down here, too?
Why did you come back for us?
The boss needs you.
More than we do.
[KENSUKE]
Take it easy, man.
We'll get to see
him soon enough.
[INAGAKI]
Good.
Now to...
Does anyone else feel that?
Captain, look!
Couldn't be.
The plane?
[KENSUKE laughs]
I bet we know who did this.
Noro?
[NORO] Hanasaki said to
come up with a "super insane
backup plan," so I did.
We couldn't get to Akeboss,
so I brought him to us.
You hacked the
Stratospheric Plane?
It'll reach the surface
in about seventeen minutes.
Just in time for sundown.
[INAGAKI] You criminals
are a threat to the order
of the nation.
Men, no need for mercy.
Kill them all!
It's all over!
Drop your weapons!
[INAGAKI] You don't have
that kind of authority!
[YOKOYANAGI] I do with
proof of criminal intent.
And your speeches
gave me all I needed.
Think for a second!
This is insurrection against
the Deputy Comm--
Anyone who overlooks crime for
such a pitiful reason is no cop!
Our job is to protect lives
and that's what I'm gonna do!
Arrest these men.
[POLICE chattering]
[NORO]
Hey, the plane stopped!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[NORO]
Someone's cut off my control!
[AKECHI]
That's enough, you guys.
[INOUE]
Akechi!
Kids shouldn't act
as shields for grown-ups.
It's the other way around.
I've been a pretty poor
excuse for a grown-up.
[INOUE]
What are you saying, boss?
Later.
[NORO]
It's rising.
Can't you re-hack
it or something?
[NORO] No! Akechi cut off
all the comm lines!
[KENSUKE]
Damn!
But we were so close!
Don't give up yet. You might
still be able to reach it.
[YAMANE]
How?
Outside.
You can use the
launch pad like a catapult.
It just might work.
[KENSUKE]
I'm lost.
How are we friends
with him again?
Think of the pad as
a big pinball machine,
and you're the ball.
[KENSUKE] You mean
we don't need the shuttle?
Bingo.
Just strap yourself in
and enjoy the ride.
Though you will fall to
your death if you miss.
Noro. Let's do this!
[NORO]
Huh?
Katsuta, I need this!
[OHTOMO]
Take these, too.
--[KENSUKE] Thank you!
--[INOUE] No, Hanasaki! Wait!
[NORO]
This is crazy! You'll die!
[KENSUKE] You wanna save
bossman, too, right?
[YOSHIO]
Wait!
Let me do this!
I'm the one who
can't die, remember?
Not this time.
It's my turn.
Sorry.
[KENSUKE]
You know, Noro...
I'm no good.
I haven't been for a while.
All I've done is rely
on everyone else.
The way I see it, this is
my only chance to truly return
to the Boy Detective's Club.
I'm taking it.
[NORO gasps]
[tires squeal]
I'm ready, Noro.
Launch me!
[NORO]
Is the airbag working?
[KENSUKE]
Good to go.
[NORO]
Once it leaves the rails,
wait for the drop in speed
then go full throttle!
[KENSUKE]
Understood.
[NORO]
If you're in trouble, tell me!
[KENSUKE]
You got it!
♪
[YOSHIO]
Screw this! Screw this!
Don't you leave me!
[NORO]
Ready?
[KENSUKE]
Yep!
[NORO]
Off you go!
♪
[NORO]
The timing must be perfect.
Punch it in three, two, one...
...now!
[KENSUKE]
Yeah!
[laughs]
[KENSUKE yelps]
[KENSUKE]
I'm not done yet!
Sorry, Kobayashi.
Couldn't keep my
promise, after all.
Hanasaki!