[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE laughs] At least
it was just my finger!
[grunts]
[KENSUKE]
Okay.
If you get within a 30cm
radius of him, it's curtains.
On that note,
please welcome Kobayashi.
If you step within this
red line, you become red paste.
No way.
Uh!
[NORO]
You're out of your mind.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
How could you invite
someone so dangerous?
It's not that bad!
As long as you keep your
distance, there's no problem!
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE gasps]
[AKECHI gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[AKECHI grunts]
Uh. Sorry.
Don't worry 'bout it.
This is my house.
You stay here,
you follow my rules.
First, your life is
your responsibility.
Hold on, boss.
Second, don't ever call me
silly titles, like "Boss".
Third, don't let
emotions rule you.
Fourth, don't disobey me.
And last, I'm the law.
End of story.
So, can you handle that?
Sure.
[AKECHI] Hey, we've got
a guest. Perfect timing.
[YOSHIO gasps]
Go. Give it all ya got, kid.
[YOSHIO]
Huh?
Huh?!
♪
[JUNKO]
I'm sorry.
It's the only recent
photo I have of him.
[INOUE] Has your son
been missing long?
[JUNKO] About three days.
He goes out often.
But, even if he's gone all day,
he always makes it
home in time for dinner.
[KENSUKE]
Hey, Granny.
[gasps]
Hush!
Did you ask the cops?
Well, no.
[KENSUKE] What made you
decide to come to us?
[INOUE sighs]
[NORO] Earth to jerk-face,
you're being rude!
Well, shouldn't you always
try the cops, first?
I'm looking after
my sick husband,
so I can't be tied
down for long periods.
Also, my son is somewhat
well-known these days,
at least to sports fans.
Wait. The Nemoto?
Didn't he get eighth
place in kayaking?
It was Sixth.
[INOUE, KENSUKE]
Mm?
[INOUE] Have you talked to any
of his co-workers or friends?
[JUNKO] Actually, Nemoto spends
most of his time at home.
[KENSUKE]
So, he's jobless?
[INOUE]
Hanasaki!
He is, I'm ashamed to say.
Should we really look for him?
Maybe he's trying
to be independent.
[AKECHI gasps]
[JUNKO] He may be a useless son,
but now that his father is ill,
if anything were to happen to
him, I don't know what I'd do.
[YOSHIO]
Then...
...just kill yourself.
[ALL gasp]
If you're suffering,
then why not?
It's not like there's
anything's stopping you.
[INOUE] Do not speak to Nao.
Don't even look at her.
I won't tolerate rudeness from
either one of you. Am I clear?
I didn't say anything wrong.
He's still a newbie,
cut him some slack.
"New" has nothing to do with it.
[grunts]
Come on, let's see a smile.
I'm totally against this.
[NORO]
That makes two of us.
[YOSHIO]
Hmph.
[knocking]
[INOUE gasps]
[children chatter]
[MIYANASHI] Here's the
missing person's report
and related documents.
All analog media, as requested.
[INOUE] You got these
together pretty fast.
Yeah, Nao just
happened to have 'em.
Not another word, Miya.
Aren't you at the end
of your rope on this?
Keep talking, and you're
handling the commission fee.
Come on. We're just talking,
there's no fee yet.
[sighs]
[NAKAMURA] One of our top
notch medical examiners
just pulled a disappearing act.
[INOUE] I see. We've both
got a missing persons' case.
All the higher-ups told us
to leave it alone, but--
I swear to God.
So how 'bout a little
give-and-take?
Our information
for some of yours?
He's nice. Unlike some people.
[INOUE] You're being
rude again, Hanasaki.
[NAKAMURA] Missing or not,
he wasn't the sort of man
who would abandon his
work out of the blue.
So what's your name, newbie?
[YOSHIO]
Hm?
[KENSUKE]
This is Kobayashi.
[NAKAMURA] Ah! Another cute
face for the boys' club, huh?
My! Akechi sure knows
how to pick'em.
[YOSHIO]
Uh...
If you had a face like that,
I wouldn't mind
having you around.
There's more to a man
than just his face.
[CHILDREN chatter, giggle]
[gasps, grunts]
--[NAKAMURA gasps]
--[MIYANASHI] Hm?
Well, see ya later!
[NAKAMURA exhales]
[KENSUKE grunts]
That was close.
[NORO] I cross-referenced
Nemo's lifestyle patterns
from just before
his disappearance,
using his credit card activity.
Convenience stores,
a net café, the park...
Looks like he never went
more than 500 meters away
from his home.
No interactions with any
friends in his recent history.
All his phone calls have been
with his mom or dad, too.
A security camera caught
some footage of him,
but nothing that will be
much help to us, sadly.
[gasps]
[footsteps]
What's up?
There's too many people.
I can't walk through.
[gasps]
[YOSHIO] Not unless you
want to make a scene.
Good point.
Okay, wait here a sec.
[INOUE]
Hm...
Did ya miss us?
I asked all over the place,
but no one's seen the guy.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[INOUE gasps]
[KENSUKE chuckles]
Wow. Graceful... Uh-oh.
Tell me, Hanasaki.
Is there anything useful
he brings to the team?
Yeah. He's invincible?
And just how is that supposed
to help us, exactly?
All I see, so far, are demerits!
[YOSHIO]
Dammit. It isn't my fault.
I didn't ask for any of this.
Kobayashi?
I told you to leave me alone!
[KENSUKE gasps]
I'll go get him.
[grunts]
Am I wrong, here?
[gasps]
Alleys, rooftops, and bridges.
So predictable.
If you want to escape,
you should change your patterns.
[YOSHIO grunts]
Ha, ha. Just kidding!
I found you because
you're wearing that.
[KENSUKE]
It's got a GPS tracker.
Finding you was easy.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE gasps]
Just stay away from me.
You wanna die, right?
[gasps]
[KENSUKE] Then at least
leave the lock open!
[YOSHIO]
Lock?
Right here.
[YOSHIO]
Uh...
[KENSUKE]
If you keep yourself closed off,
then all the effort I put
in doesn't mean jack squat.
I'm not asking
you to compromise,
just leave me an opening!
Do you understand what
I'm trying to say here?
Crack the window to your heart.
[chuckling]
[KENSUKE] What the hell?
"Window to your heart"?
That's so corny!
[YOSHIO]
I didn't say it.
[KENSUKE]
Well, anyway...
I promised I'd find a way
to kill you, and I meant it.
Just be patient, alright?
Help us out until then.
[YOSHIO]
But he...
[KENSUKE]
What? Inoue?
Don't take it personally.
He doesn't work well with
anyone younger than him.
He seems like he's in charge,
but he's actually the baby.
Hm! It's really gonna bug
me to leave things like this,
So how 'bout you and
I throw him for a loop?
[gasps]
I don't care.
Do whatever you like.
[laughs]
[MAN A]
Be quiet, damn brats!
[KENSUKE]
Uh?
[MAN A grunts]
Get that outta my face!
Oops! Sorry 'bout that.
[MAN B] If you're sorry,
then turn it off already!
Hey, perfect timing.
Have you seen this man?
He disappeared rec--
[MAN 3A]
Don't know, don't care.
Look, we're just
trying to find him.
[MAN A]
Put a sock in it!
Okay, then do you know where
some more helpful bums
might be camping out?
[MAN B]
Screw yourself!
Let's go.
[KENSUKE]
Uh.
[MAN C chuckles]
This group'll take anyone in.
If they pass a physical.
Per...
Thanks for the tip, mister!
[YOSHIO, KENSUKE]
Hm?
How about a tip
for me, little man?
[YOSHIO gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE] At Persephone,
we offer on-going support
for the hopeless
in their old age.
Cast off your loneliness,
and leave fear behind.
Our facilities--
[NORO] Sounds like a super
shady group, if you ask me.
But, I guess if you're
the target audience,
it probably sounds
like paradise.
[NORO]
To put it in terms that someone
with the intellect
of a sea slug, like you,
can understand, they protect
the dignity of the hopeless.
They even get free
food and shelter.
[KENSUKE]
Mm-hm! I totally get it.
[NORO]
You don't, but whatever.
We just need to know
if our target is here.
Anything else is a distraction.
Aren't you gonna thank
Kobayashi for getting this info?
Wasn't planning on it.
He's been pretty useful.
He deserves some credit.
Answers come first.
Aw, come on!
Enough. Don't try to meddle.
You're cool with that?
[FRONT DESK WOMAN]
I'm sorry, sir.
We can't allow visitors if
the resident they're visiting
hasn't given prior consent.
[INOUE] Can you at least
tell us if Kouichi Nemoto
is staying here?
[FRONT DESK WOMAN 3A]
Policy forbids me to answer
such questions in order to
protect our resident's privacy.
Come on, lady, give us
something to work with here.
I'm very sorry, sir.
You really can't,
no matter what?
Don't make me call security.
I'll build in a
shrine in your honor!
Please, just throw
me a freakin' bone!
Well, that didn't work.
You're up.
Smash through the wall!
Huh?
Just walk up to it,
and Ka-boom! Cool?
That won't be necessary.
[YOSHIO, KENSUKE]
Hm?
You got a better plan?
You can climb, can't you?
[KENSUKE chuckles]
What's my time?
[NORO]
Forty-two seconds.
I guess that's about right.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[laughs]
[NORO]
How incompetent can you get?
[KENSUKE]
No kidding.
[NORO]
It's no laughing matter.
[YOSHIO grunts, pants]
Right. Let's get going.
[YOSHIO]
Hm.
[KENSUKE]
Knock, knock.
Huh?
[INOUE]
Still waiting on the layout.
Keep your shirt on.
[KENSUKE whistles]
[PIPPO hoots]
[KENSUKE]
A net café?
[YOSHIO]
More like a barn.
[NORO]
I'll use facial recognition
to see if Nemo's in there.
Was that?
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
Those are the missing people
from Nakamura's files.
I'm sure of it.
Really?
[YOSHIO grunts]
None of them have had work
for at least ten years.
They've been living by
leeching off their parents.
In millennial terms,
they're textbook NEETs .
[NORO]
As far as I can tell,
every one of them is a deadbeat,
through and through.
And all of their parents
are either dead,
in hospice, or a nursing home.
Sounds like they'd get
along with kayak guy.
[INOUE] There'd be no
end to it if the police tried
to investigate
every one of them.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[INOUE]
What now?
I didn't do anything. The wall--
Nothing to worry about.
I just tripped.
We'll let you know if
we find him, okay?
Sup, old man?
What the-- Hey!
So why are you in this place?
Is it against your will?
Security! What's goin' on?
There's a kid in here!
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[MAN 3D] This is my room,
you little brat! Get out! Now!
--[alarm buzzes]
--[YOSHIO] Move it!
--[KENSUKE grunts] Crap!
[SECURITY GUARDS shouting]
[KENSUKE]
Yikes.
So what do we do?
You're getting into this,
aren't you?
You wanna take 'em out?
You know I don't want that.
[KENSUKE] Then we'll have to
find some way around them.
[OLD MAN A]
Get in.
Huh?
[SECURITY OFFICERS chatter]
Thanks for the save.
This place wasn't meant
to be a playground.
You kids should just run home.
Sure. We'll do that.
Right after we find this guy.
Does he look familiar?
[OLD MAN A]
When did he disappear?
[KENSUKE] Uh...
Something like three days ago?
[OLD MAN A] Then he'd still
be going through the tests.
[KENSUKE]
Tests?
[OLD MAN 3A] Applicants have
to pass a physical exam
and an acceptance test to know
whether they'll fit in here.
Check the floor below us.
Heh! Thank you.
Hey. Why are you here, anyway?
[OLD MAN A]
It's comfortable here.
I don't have to look
anyone in the face.
[OLD MAN A]
If I die,
they'll take care of my body
without telling anyone.
I think I understand why
it appealed to you.
[YOSHIO]
Tsk. I don't understand them.
Why would these people
be so determined to live,
they'd stay in this place?
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
They might as well die.
Make it easy on themselves.
But dying is scary.
And besides--
[gasps]
You don't know if dying will
solve anything. How could you?
[gasps]
[KENSUKE chuckles]
Don't get mad, dude.
You know I'm right.
[OLD MAN A grunts]
[YOSHIO]
Look!
[KENSUKE]
Hm?
[OLD MAN A grunts]
Stop.
[grunting continues]
[KENSUKE]
Old man!
[LAB MAN A]
Type B-positive en route.
[KENSUKE, YOSHIO gasp]
[INOUE]
Hm?
[KENSUKE] Something's wrong
with this place.
One of the geezers
was just carted off.
[INOUE]
Did you forget the mission?
Huh?
[INOUE] Our priority is
finding Kouichi Nemoto!
[grunts]
To hell with that!
He's gone rogue again.
[INOUE] His call.
Let him deal with it.
Right. I'll do that.
[KENSUKE, YOSHIO pant, grunt]
[KENSUKE]
Grab on!
[YOSHIO grunts]
[KENSUKE grunts]
So many.
Tsk.
[BOTH gasp]
[KENSUKE]
The hell is all this?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Let him go!
[SECURITY OFFICER A]
Stop!
[SECURITY OFFICER B]
Don't move!
[KYOUMOTO]
Sorry about that.
[YOSHIO, KENSUKE gasps]
[KYOUMOTO]
If you'd gotten any closer,
your bacteria could ruin
these perfectly good organs.
That's what you were
planning to do with him?
[KYOUMOTO] All of our
residents will help us save
countless lives.
Compared to spending their
last years in idleness
and shame, this is a far
better use of their bodies.
[KYOUMOTO]
Now, why don't you boys
forget about what you saw
and just run on home?
[INOUE]
Kobayashi.
[gasps]
Huh?
[INOUE]
Let me see his face.
Tell Kensuke.
[INOUE]
Just do it.
Like this?
It's him!
The medical examiner Inspector
Nakamura was looking for!
[NORO]
No way!
[KYOUMOTO] All vermin are
looking for a good place to die.
I'm simply helping them
to find that place.
We have the same interests.
I told you these people
wanted to end it all.
[NORO] God, you're dumb.
The kind of people who'd stay
in this place don't have the
guts to live, let alone die.
[YOSHIO gasps]
Don't call me dumb.
[KENSUKE whistles]
[KYOUMOTO]
Uh! What is that?
They caught us. Now what?
I'm glad you asked.
We cause trouble!
[KYOUMOTO chuckles]
[gasps]
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[PIPPO hoots]
[NORO]
Hey, Koba! Heads up!
Uh, Koba?
[MAN E]
Huh? What's this?
[yells]
[MEN chattering]
[NORO]
Run, boys!
[KYOUMOTO]
Get downstairs, now!
[SECURITY OFFICER B]
Right!
[grunting]
[KYOUMOTO grunts]
Brat!
[KENSUKE chuckles]
[DOCTORS gasp]
[KYOUMOTO growls]
Put everything on lock down!
Don't let them get outside!
[LAB MEN shout]
[KENSUKE]
Kobayashi.
Do your thing.
But I don't want to.
Unlock your freakin' window!
[YOSHIO]
Tsk.
[DOCTOR B pants]
--[DOCTOR B groans]
--[LAB MEN shout]
[YOSHIO]
That wasn't my fault, okay?
[KYOUMOTO] Don't just
stand there, grab him!
Make a break for it!
The truth's out there,
no matter what you do now.
[KYOUMOTO]
Huh?
Our club's professional shut-in
just sent that video to every
cop in the city.
Sucks to be you.
[gasps]
[police sirens blaring]
[MEN shouting]
[NEMOTO pants]
Search target captured!
Get offa me, ya gimp!
[NEMOTO groans]
Please, sir. Don't make this
any harder than it has to be.
[NEMOTO grunts]
You just had to butt in.
[JUNKO]
Please come home.
Fine, but I'm not helpin'
you take care of the old man,
got it?
Jerk.
Was this really worth
saving a guy like him?
[KENSUKE] Mm... I don't really
think about that stuff.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[NAKAMURA]
It's true that Kyoumoto
once worked for our department,
but that isn't the case anymore.
His crimes are clear,
and I promise that he will be
prosecuted to the
fullest extent of the law.
Hey, keep your chin up.
[NAKAMURA]
Stop talking.
[MIYANASHI grunts]
[INOUE]
Kobayashi is dangerous!
[grunts]
Huh?
[INOUE] His power could
injure or kill someone,
and he doesn't even know
how to keep it under control!
[NORO] Not to mention
he's a total freakazoid.
[KENSUKE] Hey, you don't
have any room to talk, Noro.
You flip out whenever
someone calls you a shut-in.
[INOUE] It's only a matter of
time before he makes a mess
that we won't be
able to clean up.
[AKECHI]
Nao can take care of it.
[INOUE]
You can't be serious!
Powers or not, the kid's the
only one that followed my rules.
Huh?
[AKECHI] Hanasaki, you let
your emotions rule you
and acted on your own instead
of sticking to the job.
And it worked, didn't it?
[AKECHI] Noro, whether a member
of this team lives or dies
is their own responsibility,
but you came running to
me for help, didn't you?
[NORO]
Because Hanasaki's a--
[AKECHI] Inoue. You insist
on calling me stupid
titles like "boss".
Cut it out already.
This is no time for jokes.
Stuff it! I'm the law,
you got that?
ou, on the other hand,
followed my rules.
So you can stay with us.
End of story.
Yes! Awesome!
[INOUE growls]
[YOSHIO gasps]
I don't care either way.
[KENSUKE]
Hm.
So, you wanna play? I do.
♪
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Underground Labyrinth."