[gunshot]
[KENSUKE gasps]
[grunts]
[YOSHIO continues gasping]
[ARISU'S MOTHER gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
[YOSHIO]
It hurts!
♪
Kobayashi!
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Hold it!
[KENSUKE]
Why? Why did you do that?
[INOUE] He's bleeding
too much. If this keeps up.
Guess his wish came true.
Your little race
has come to an end.
[grunts]
[KENSUKE]
No matter what it takes,
one day, I'll kill you.
[grunts]
Dammit! I didn't want this!
[AKECHI] See that?
He's losing his juice.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
This power always kept
him from killing himself.
So, why did it suddenly
decide to let him?
You mean he?
[AKECHI] Yeah. It's the only
thing that makes sense.
[KENSUKE]
What does? I don't get it!
[grunts]
[INOUE] His ability to
prevent death. It's possible,
it has a direct correllation
with his desire to die.
If that desire were to fade,
so would his power.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[AKECHI] In simple terms.
Kobayashi wants to live.
Poor kid.
[gasps]
[KENSUKE] This is messed up.
What's your deal, huh?
You're always telling me
to hurry up and kill you.
[AKECHI]
Who knows?
Maybe he thought you were fun
to be around. Worth living for.
[gasps]
I've got a theory.
Remember the times you got hurt?
[KENSUKE] First at the factory,
then at the venue hall.
Both after you helped someone.
So if we solve a bunch of cases,
you can get hurt
a bunch of times
and finally kick the bucket!
You mean. It was never about
solving cases. It was me?
[KENSUKE grunts]
No. No. It's not fair!
[AKECHI sighs]
[AKECHI grunts] If we can't
touch him, we can't treat him,
let alone carry him out of here.
[KENSUKE]
Then what do we do?
[AKECHI] As much as I
loathe to suggest it.
The only way to save him now
is to make him want to die.
[KENSUKE gasps]
If we can do that,
his power'll save his life.
Though that might be crueler
than just letting him go.
[KENSUKE] How're we
supposed to choose for him?
You're the one who
made Koba wanna live
in the first place.
It's your call.
[KENSUKE grunts]
Whatever you decide,
I won't be any part of it.
[KENSUKE]
Huh?
[AKECHI]
Don't follow me around anymore.
[INOUE]
Boss, wait.
[AKECHI] The Boy Detective's
club is disbanded.
[KENSUKE gasps]
[INOUE grunts]
Disbanded? Why?
[NORO gasps]
[ARISU'S MOTHER grunts]
[gun clicks]
Don't even try it.
[ARISU'S MOTHER gasps]
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[HIDE] Where the hell
have you been, lady?
We were looking everywhere.
And, by the way, what was with
all that trigger happy nonsense?
You said you'd only
use it for revenge.
The last time I checked, this
cop didn't murder your daughter.
[NAKAMURA] Who are you?
What's your involvement here?
[HIDE] Sorry, miss. Wish I
could stick around and chat,
but she and I have a date
with a getaway car.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[gasps]
[KENSUKE gasps]
[NORO]
Inoue.
Did Akechi tell you he was
going to break up the club?
We'll talk about that later.
[NORO]
You kept me out of the loop?
After everything we've
been through together?
I said later, Noro!
[NORO]
No! You owe me that much!
If you've got some excuse,
I want to hear it!
[gasps]
[NORO]
Inoue!
[INOUE grunts]
[NORO gasps]
What are you doing?
[INOUE grunts]
It'll work.
I don't follow.
Grab the curtain!
[KENSUKE]
Uh...
[gasps]
[INOUE]
We'll pick him up with this
and put him in my wheelchair.
Understood.
[INOUE]
Be careful.
If we drop him,
we're out of options.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[police sirens blaring]
Put an APB out! They've already
got a head start.
[MIYANISHI]
Hey, boss.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
You're late.
[MIYANISHI grunts]
Gee, thanks for the concern.
It's not like I broke out of
the hospital or anything.
You could at least try
to praise me a little bit.
[NAKAMURA grunts]
The case is over. Or is it?
[MIYANISHI]
Huh?
[BOSS D]
Nakamura!
[NAKAMURA, MIYANASHI gasp]
[BOSS D growls]
Shoot me.
[BOSS D] I knew you'd find
a way to screw this up.
I have half a mind to make you
a meter maid for the rest
of your career, but you'd
probably screw that up, too!
[NAKAMURA]
Miyanishi, come here.
[MIYANISHI]
Hm?
[BOSS D]
...stop making trouble for--
[BOSS D growls]
Nakamura! Over here. Now!
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[MIYANISHI]
hm?
[NORO] Should I send the
car to the back entrance?
Sure.
[NORO]
I'm on it.
Go.
[KENSUKE gasps]
When the car gets here, take
Kobayashi back to the office.
[KENSUKE grunts]
You don't want the police
finding him, right?
Good point.
Then...
[KENSUKE grunts]
Don't worry about me.
Just get going.
Huh?! No freakin' way. Come on!
[KENSUKE gasps]
Go!
[KENSUKE exhales]
[INOUE, KENSUKE gasp]
Uh. Hey. This a bad time?
I can always come back later.
[grunts]
[INOUE] Sorry. You shouldn't
be doing this when you're hurt.
[MIYANISHI] This?
Just a scratch. No biggie.
Besides, this is hardly the
time to be worrying about me.
Still, we appreciate the help.
But, why are you here?
[MIYANISHI] Huh? Oh, Nakamura
sent me to check on you guys.
Nakamura did?
Yeah. She's a little bit
occupied at the moment.
[BOSS D] You know what
you are? An embarrassment!
This is exactly why I was
against this operation
from the beginning!
That damn detective agency,
or club, whatever the
hell they are.
Yet you hired them and
what happened? Disaster!
[NAKAMURA]
I know. This is all my fault.
I'll take full responsibility.
[BOSS D]
Damn right you will.
Finally, something we
can agree on.
However, don't you dare
think you're the only one
who has to shoulder
this disgrace. We all do!
The entire police force.
Hope you're happy!
[grunts]
[MIYANISHI]
Going to the office?
Move over, I can
drive you there.
No, you've already done plenty.
We couldn't possibly
ask anymore of you.
Besides...
[INOUE]
...this is our problem.
[HIDE hums]
[humming continues]
[HIDE chuckles]
[HIDE grunts]
Stop by the hideout first so
we can drop off the old lady.
And then?
You really need to ask?
We make a house call.
[YOSHIO gasps]
[YOSHIO grunts]
Kobayashi!
[KENSUKE]
Take this!
It's medicine! Hold out
your hand. Hurry!
[YOSHIO gasps]
Come on! It'll help you!
I can't give it to you.
[KENSUKE] Do you understand?
You gotta do it yourself.
Take it, Koba. Please?
Please! Kobayashi,
take the freaking pill!
[KENSUKE gasps]
Damn you!
[NORO] Isn't there
anything you can do?
[INOUE]
If there were, I'd do it.
[KENSUKE grunts, growls]
[KENSUKE]
Dammit. Dammit!
[KENSUKE sobs]
The only way to save him now
is to make him want to die.
How the hell am supposed
to do that, Boss?
You made it
sound easy. It's not!
[KENSUKE grunts]
[KENSUKE, INOUE gasp]
[gasps]
How's it goin?
[KENSUKE]
Why are you here?
What a silly question.
I came to get you, of course.
Huh?
It's party time!
Not really.
We're going over the failed
mission and licking our wounds.
[NORO]
Huh? What's happening?
You know this person?
Uh... Yeah?
[HIDE laughs]
That's the guy, right?
The invincible badass?
Dude... Whoa!
He's bleedin' like crazy!
I'm confused. I thought
he could deflect bullets
with his mind or something.
How'd he get hurt?
Wait. When you said "failed
mission", did you mean Fukiya?
Yup. An eye for an eye.
The whole point of this
operation was to get revenge
for the girl's family.
You organized this catastrophe?
Uh... Organizing ain't my style.
More like, "volunteered
to help out".
This is serious!
Why all the secrecy?
[KENSUKE grunts]
Well, I...
[HIDE] Y'mean, Han didn't
tell you about any of this?
No, he didn't.
[KENSUKE gasps]
Why'd you hide this from us?
[KENSUKE]
I wasn't hiding it!
Besides, I ditched them--
[INOUE]
Making excuses?
I don't need them.
Tell it to Kobayashi.
[KENSUKE exhales]
[INOUE] He's got one foot
in the grave because of you.
Give the guy a break, man.
He had literally
nothing to do with this.
It was just a
weird twist of fate.
No one asked you.
This is our problem.
Stay out of it!
[HIDE grunts] 'Fraid I
can't go along with that.
No matter what happened,
Han is a life-time member of
Hide and the Hooligans.
[KENSUKE, INOUE gasp]
[INOUE]
So that's how it is, huh?
[KENSUKE grunts]
[INOUE]
Must feel good, Kensuke.
You made new friends.
How nice for you.
[KENSUKE gasps] You don't
have to put it like that!
I was hurting. I... just wanted
things to feel normal.
Then... I realized it'd
never be the same again.
I've changed and
I can't undo it.
[KENSUKE sniffs] And I'm not
the only one who changed!
No good stayin' here, Han.
Come with me and we'll Par-tay!
Ugh. I really need to stop that.
[HIDE gasps] Hey, I'm the
leader! I go first!
[INOUE sighs]
[AKECHI] The Boy Detective's
club is disbanded.
Dammit, boss, you didn't
have to come out and say it.
I think we already
knew the truth.
After all...
...you left and you
didn't look back.
[YOSHIO grunts]
[INOUE gasps]
[grunting continues]
♪
[TWENTY-FACES chuckles]
I wonder.
Do you think your new
toy could give me
the thrills I crave, Akechi?
[TWENTY-FACES]
"Mistaken Absolute Evil."