Thanks hon...
Excuse me, what are you eating?
You mean to tell
me you don't know
what Soba noodles are?
Huh.
I would like to
try some of these...
Noodles.
What's wrong with him?
Mister Krory here...
He wanted to try Soba
noodles but he did it all wrong.
He thought the
won ton was bread...
...the dipping sauce, soup...
and the noodles, Italian pasta!
He ate each of them separately,
and then had the smart idea
to eat a mouth full of wasabi...
It was the worst food
I had ever tasted in my life!
Kanda you should have taught
him how to eat it correctly.
I don't have time to babysit,
unlike you apparently.
You're done eatin' already...?
Do you have an
assignment to get to?
I'm heading to Denmark
on a mission soon.
Well at least
you're staying busy, Yu.
How many times have I told you
not to call me by that name?
Woah there...
Speaking of missions, hey Allen!
I ran into Chief Komui earlier
and he said he
wanted to see you.
Yeah...?
Maybe the Chief's got
a mission for me too...
Huh.
You want me to
act as a courier...?
So I guess there's no mission?
Yeah...
Sorry to throw this on you
so soon after your return
but I need you to deliver
this to General Yeegar.
And he can be found
somewhere in the Netherlands.
He's the oldest of all
the Black Order Generals,
however he's a born soldier
who's spent his entire
career on the front line.
Uh, uh...
Would you mind if
I asked you a question...?
This General Yeegar, is
he an eccentric person,
like my old master?
Gee uh... I'm not sure...
The one thing I know is
he's very particular
about proper manners.
So you may want to
study up on your etiquette.
I really don't want
to go on this trip...
Why'd he have to pick me?
Why have you sent Allen Walker
on a simple courier
mission to General Yeegar?
The General sent me a request
to see Allen a few days ago...
He said he wanted to see the boy
who was prophesized by Hevlaska
as the Destroyer of Time
with his own eyes.
I see...
I guess we can assume
the General is becoming
concerned about his own future?
Yes... and... about
Allen's left eye as well.
He's worried the Earl
may act against it...
and then, the one who
stands to lose the most
would be Allen as a consequence.
It's gotten darker.
And it's looking more
and more like the
marking of an Akuma.
I used to believe
that having an eye
like Allen's would be a
huge advantage in our fight.
But I just think back
to the day I saw the soul
of an Akuma in person and I
gotta say, it's not worth it...
It was tough to look at.
The sight of it
turned my stomach
so bad I couldn't keep
food down for days...
The world Allen
sees every day... is hell.
Someone's supposed to meet me
at this station but how
long is that going to take?
You must be Allen Walker.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Thierry.
I'm a Finder with the unit
assigned to General Yeegar.
So Thierry, I guess you
know who I am already...
Thanks for coming out
this way to pick me up.
I appreciate it...
I'm on a courier mission.
Chief Komui back at
Headquarters instructed me
to give this over
to General Yeegar.
Oh dear... I'm terribly
sorry to inform you
but the General
is no longer here.
Huh?
He made his way towards Belgium
the other day the moment
he heard there was innocence
discovered in the area.
Belgium, well... uh...
The border's not
too far from here.
The train isn't coming, is it?
Well, let's just say it's
not coming any time soon...
I'd give it another
two hours or so.
So... Chief Komui told me that
the General is strict when
it comes to manners.
Do you find that to be the case?
Yeah sure, I mean
sometimes he can be
a stickler for table manners
and proper language,
but I've worked
around him long enough
to know he's a really nice guy.
What...?
He's a nice guy...?
The General?!
Um... why the sudden outburst?
Oh, Forgive me...
It's just that I have
trouble equating the words
nice guy when talking about a
General of any kind, that's all.
Help...
I'd rather lose a thumb
than go back there!
General Yeeger is a
genuine and kind leader...
He knows a wide
variety of subjects...
and he teaches us about them.
For instance, do
you know the species
of this particular butterfly?
No.
This one is a form
of Nymphalidae...
It's commonly found in
Europe, and western Asia.
And General Yeegar
taught you about that?
Yes, it's one of the many
things he's taught us.
How should I put it...
The General acts as somewhat
of a mentor to us all...
I've heard that before
he joined the Order
he taught young children,
so maybe it's natural for him.
He sounds like a
really great guy...
I look forward to
meeting with him.
So there's Innocence
in this town?
Yes, we're absolutely
certain there's Innocence
somewhere within the city...
However the location
of General Yeegar
is still somewhat up in the air.
It's too bad there's no one here
to ask if they've seen him.
Listen Thierry...
We need to contact
General Yeegar right away.
Why?
If he's still within the city,
the wireless Golem should
be able to reach him...
Grab it.
That's... a problem...
General Yeegar doesn't
have a Golem anymore.
Huh?
I'm afraid his Golem
stopped working recently
and he never got a new one...
I was hoping
perhaps the contents
of that case of yours
has a replacement.
Do we have another
way of contacting him?
No, not from here...
though if he
contacted headquarters
since we've left he may have
notified them of his position,
in which case we can use
that to track him down.
We don't have time
to contact headquarters,
which is why I think we should
continue our search on foot,
at least for the time being.
Why are you acting so aggitated?
Is there something
I should know?
It's the way the
townspeople are acting.
I've seen that look before.
It's an Akuma.
The scent that was
unleashed when the Innocence
was discovered has attracted
the Akuma to this town.
You sure?
Persistent!
Persistent! Persistent!
You really are tenacious...
You know that?!
There's nowhere to escape...
Return the Innocence
you murdered for at once,
before I make the end
of your existence hell.
You sure you want
to be making threats...
To my friends?!
Go ahead and take it
from me if you can.
I guess you're not smart
enough to listen to reason.
You've left me with no choice!
Oh wow, what a
tough-talking grandpa you are!
I hope you don't
break your hip...
Get him!
There he is!
Amazing.
You don't know when to quit!
I'm through showing
you mercy, old man!
Wait! What the... NO!
Bastards...! No no no no no!!!
Any last words?
I should ask the same for you...
DIE!!!
General Yeegar, just
stay where you are!
I'll handle him from here!
I take it you're Allen Walker...
I'd like to thank
you for... saving me...
You are brave.
Ohh, it was nothing.
I was amazed
at your abilities...
I'm glad you're safe...
and that you were able to
re-capture the Innocence.
At a price... yes...
But, many innocent people
have lost their lives here.
Had we acted sooner,
then the loss of
life in your town
would have been avoided
and for that I apologize...
Please forgive me.
An apology isn't
necessary sir...
Because you reacted
at all, many more lives
have been saved that would
have otherwise been lost.
We appreciate what
you've done for us
from the bottom of our hearts...
We will forever be in your debt.
So you're General Cross'
apprentice, isn't that right?
Uhh... yes.
I've heard training under
him can be hellacious.
Yeah, that's about right...
But don't take
that the wrong way!
It was worth it...
I appreciate everything
Master Cross did for me.
Cross is an interesting fellow.
As a human being
he needs some work
and lacks a variety
of social graces,
but, no one is more attuned
to the extermination of Akuma.
Huh?
I believe that is why he
made you his apprentice.
Because you've housed Innocence
within your body since birth.
As you already know,
each of us five Generals
carry several pieces
of Innocence with us in the
field at all times in order
to seek out worthy
Accommodators.
Including the Innocence
I collected today,
I have eight pieces
in my possession.
I don't know how many
more pieces I can collect
before putting myself in danger,
nor do I know the amount
of Accommodators I can find
in the little time
I have left in this world,
but to end this war,
I must continue the
quest for Innocence.
Now please, eat...
This is how I choose
to show my appreciation.
General...
I didn't do anything to
deserve this... kindness.
This meal is not a
thanks for saving me...
But in honor of
becoming an Exorcist
and enduring its hardships.
Though you're a full-fledged
member of The Order,
it is often difficult to
deal with the horrors of war
especially as young as you are.
The least you deserve for making
such a profound
sacrifice to the Order
is a good meal
every now and then.
Thank you General Yeegar.
This is delicious...!
Best meal I've ever had
and this bread! Oh the bread!
Oh... that's great...
I'm glad you like it.
I do... I do!
Unbelievable.
It's quite common actually,
the hosts of Parasite Type
Accommodator's tend
to have abnormally large
appetites, as you can see...
Very impressive...
I'm sorry...
I cleared the table.
Oh, no!
Don't worry about it son.
Eat as much as you
like. I don't mind.
Eating an abundant
amount of food
is a wonderful complement to
a cook so please, eat your fill.
He is just like you had
described him Thierry.
General Yeegar,
he's a really nice guy,
just like you were telling me...
Sir you must have
been a fantastic
teacher back in the day.
I'm sure all of your
students couldn't wait to get
to school every morning
to learn from the best.
Actually...
I wasn't a good teacher by
any stretch of the imagination.
Huh?
Because...
I was unable to protect them...
at a time when my
students needed me the most.
So what happened...?
Don't tell me...
Did you...?
Yes...
It happened forty years ago
though it seems like yesterday.
I was in a small village
in the country working
as a school teacher...
I had just under
twenty students,
allowing me to give each
of them my full attention.
They responded
quite well to this
and we formed a strong bond.
However, it wasn't long before
tragedy struck our class.
It changed us all forever.
One day, a female student
passed away suddenly
from a serious illness...
Everyone in our class
mourned her death,
but no one suffered more
from her passing
than her best friend...
Joanne.
The day after he took
advantage of her grief.
Why good evening there... child.
The Millennium Earl.
He manipulated Joanne
in her moment of weakness
and brought her friends soul
back turning her into an Akuma.
Her classmates were
unaware of what had happened
and were happy for
Joanne when she returned
after her long absence of
grieving for her friend.
Feeling better now Joanne?
Hey Joanne, you
look a little pale.
That's okay.
We'll help cheer you up!
What I saw that day was
the most horrific scene
I'd ever laid eyes on...
Most of the students were dead,
but those that were
still clinging to life,
suffered greatly
before expiring.
I panicked, just like anyone
in that situation would,
and ran out to the
schoolyard to call for help.
And then...
I saw Joanne
standing in the yard,
facing a man who was aiming
an arrow straight at her head.
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
That man turned out to be an
Exorcist with the Black Order.
I suppose he saw
something in me,
because after explaining
what an Akuma was,
he suggested I go to the
Order where it was revealed
that I was an
Accommodator of Innocence,
and could become an Exorcist.
The last forty years of my life
have been dedicated
to fighting evil
and preventing tragedies like
this from ever happening again.
However...
the fight of one old man
is not nearly enough.
It seems as though
you have been through
many hardships as
well... Allen Walker.
Yes, sir, I have...
I turned Mana into an Akuma...
He was someone who
was very special to me.
Then I destroyed
what he became...
That's when my left eye received
the curse it bears now...
Allowing me to see
the souls of Akuma.
I heard...
I also heard that soon after
you became Cross' apprentice
and began your
Exorcist training.
At first I wanted to
become an Exorcist
to atone for Mana's death.
But now I know
better than that...
Because I fight in
order to survive,
to ensure that the people
who have died can rest easy,
to make every day worth living.
Some people would see being born
with Innocence in
their body a curse...
Whereas I see it as my fate.
The fact is...
I turned the most
important person in my life
into an Akuma so the
only thing I can do is...
There's no need
to explain yourself...
I believe you handled
your situation bravely,
young man...
I am proud to know you
for that reason alone.
Thank you, General.
Trust me, I understand how you
and Joanne felt
compelled to bring back
the soul of someone you loved.
No one can blame you
for reacting the
way that you did...
Even the most righteous
exorcist would understand.
Remember, that
knowing firsthand the pain
and suffering one goes
through when confronted
with the Earl and his
deception can only aid
in your journey as an Exorcist.
That knowledge will enable
you to save more lives
than you could
ever have imagined.
Allen, are you all right?
It's nothing really.
I'm okay... I'm sorry.
It wasn't a mistake...
It wasn't...
I became an Exorcist
for a reason, right Mana?
Take care you guys!
You humans continue to fight
even though you have
no future in this world...
It's pathetic.
What are you talking about?
I have a message for you
from Lord Millennium.
Your time has come...
The seven thousand year
prologue has finally ended,
and the play is about to begin.
Don't miss the rising
of the curtain...!
For you are the
actors... the Exorcists!
If that's true then
everything up to this point
was just a ruse.
♪ The Lord Millennium
is in search of you. ♪
♪ Looking for the heart now,
have you heard the news? ♪
♪ Maybe you stole
it from him. ♪
♪ I'll see if it's true. ♪
The Millennium Earl
has announced
his intentions to bring
about the end of mankind.
As the starting bell rings,
a beginning too cruel
to describe unfolds.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The Beginning of the End"!
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.