Hevlaska!
[LEVEL 4]
How lucky can I be?
There's even more humans
here than I thought.
[LAVI]
Damn it.
[LENALEE] Every night as I'm
falling asleep in my bed,
I wish for the same thing.
That the next morning
I'll wake up
only to discover that this
was all just a dream.
[LENALEE] In this world,
there was no holy war.
No Millennium Earl. Akuma.
Even the Exorcists
never existed.
They were only the
products of a nightmare.
[sighs]
[LENALEE] I sigh in relief
and think to myself,
"Good. It was all just a dream."
[LENALEE] From nearby,
I hear Komui calling my name.
And then I notice the telltale
signs he's cooking breakfast.
[LENALEE] It's like the
end of a bad novel.
No conflict. Shallow characters.
Barely any resolution.
The kind of story that
would disappoint readers.
[KOMUI]
Uhh...
[chuckles]
[LENALEE] But I don't care
how ridiculous it sounds.
I've imagined this scene
a thousand times.
[LENALEE]
I-Inno... cence.
Please.
God, I've hated you for so
long, but hear me, please.
I'm begging you...
Give me strength.
Look at me. I want
to see your eyes.
[LENALEE]
Never...
Never before in my life
have I wanted Innocence
as much as I do now.
[LENALEE grunts]
[ROUVELIER]
Huh?
[gasps]
Look at me.
So Walker made it out alive.
[LEVEL 4]
Very strange.
How you can still move around
after what I did to you?
Last time we met, you
looked defeated to me.
Allen, no!
Allen!
These injuries...
How can you move?
You should be knocked out!
[KOMUI] His Crown Clown. It's
acting like a suit of armor.
[gasps]
[KOMUI] Somehow his Innocence
is controlling his body.
Forcibly moving it!
Allen, wait!
I'm tired of feeling helpless.
Needing saving.
Lenalee.
Has she started synchronizing
with her Innocence?
[LAVI]
Go to her, Komui.
She lives and fights
because of you.
You know that, don't you?
Go and stand beside her, Chief.
You're her big brother.
[KOMUI]
I want to.
But I don't know what to do!
What good would it bring?
[KANDA] What the hell
are you talkin' about?
How pathetic! You make me sick!
What's the matter?
Lose your sister complex?
[KOMUI]
Hey. Why did you kick me?
Can you even tell me the reason
why you joined the Black Order?
[KOMUI]
I'm home.
[KOMUI] I'll be living
here with you from now on.
[LENALEE]
Big brother.
I'm home.
Welcome back,
my sweet little sister.
[LENALEE]
I'm-I'm home.
Have a safe trip!
I'll see you later!
[chuckles]
[KOMUI]
Welcome home.
Lenalee.
[JOHNNY]
Here she is!
It's good to see
you home, Lenalee!
Good to be home.
Welcome back, sis.
There's no place like home, huh?
[LENALEE]
Those days are long gone.
I'm not that little girl
crying in bed anymore.
I've got my brother and
everyone else at home.
That alone gives me the will to
fight in this nightmarish world.
Innocence... if you can turn
my emotions into strength
so I can protect
everyone I care about,
I vow... I'll follow you.
Right until the
very end. Anywhere.
[LENALEE]
But... still...
No matter what happens...
[LENALEE] In the end,
I'll come home to my brother.
I promise.
See you later, big brother!
[LENALEE]
Please tell me, "See you soon."
Until the day... when I smile
and say... "I'm home again."
[KOMUI]
She drank it!
Lenalee!
[LENALEE groaning]
[KOMUI]
Lenalee!
She's bleeding?
[ROUVELIER]
The body's rejecting it?
Allen Walker!
[ALLEN]
Take cover!
[laughing]
[LEVEL 4] I have more fun
for you! Puny Exorcist!
[yells]
Don't lose your footing!
You're the only one who
can fight right now!
[ALL yelling]
Lenalee.
[KOMUI]
Do something!
Hold on. I'll check.
Don't touch her feet.
[HEVLASKA] To think that
you swallowed it. Lenalee.
[KOMUI]
Don't blame her!
The Innocence turned
into liquid on its own.
It's as though it was
saying "drink me!"
[ROUVELIER]
Has the Innocence come to dwell
inside Lenalee's body?
Has it or hasn't it, Hevlaska?
Why hasn't the bleeding stopped?
Lenalee!
[yells]
Allen!
What fun. He still
hasn't had enough yet.
[yells]
Yu!
Now, short stack!
[yells]
It stopped the blade?
[LEVEL 4]
That won't do at all.
If you want to play rough,
why didn't you say so
in the first place?!
Let's play rough!
[LAVI screams]
[LEVEL 4]
You're not tired, are you?
I'm not finished playing
with you just yet.
Allen, no!
Hevlaska! How does it look?
[HEVLASKA]
What can this mean?
What's the matter?
[HEVLASKA]
It's gone.
She may have swallowed
her Innocence,
and I detect signs that it
passed through her body,
but I am completely unable
to sense it within her.
[ROUVELIER]
What? That can't be true!
[HEVLASKA]
It's gone. It's not in her body.
Where then?
[KOMUI]
Her blood, it's--
[gasps]
That's impossible.
My Innocence.
You sensed it, didn't you?
That I'm prepared.
Amazing. I've never seen
anything like this.
The innocence is weaponizing
itself with Lenalee's blood.
Activate.
You managed to
entertain me. Even so...
Time to say goodbye!
How dare you enter our home
and try to destroy it!
Wanna play too?
[LENALEE]
It's gonna fire.
Allen! Lenalee!
That was a direct hit!
You're wrong. I didn't hit them.
There you are!
[LAVI]
They flew up that high?
Kanda, did you see them?
Too fast for my eyes.
[ALLEN]
Way too fast.
[LENALEE]
Huh? I'm sorry!
I hope it didn't make you sick!
[LENALEE]
That's strange.
I wasn't trying
to jump this high.
I must be getting used to the
Dark Boots again and misjudged.
Is that a butterfly?
[LENALEE yells]
I'll be all right.
You shouldn't be afraid
to let go of me, Lenalee.
I'll extend the Clown Belt
to prevent me from falling.
There's one more thing.
Back in Lab Five,
I couldn't protect everyone.
I'm sorry.
[LENALEE] I'm sorry, too.
For getting here so late.
You ready to stop it?
[ALLEN]
Here we go!
I'm waiting!
[ROUVELIER] Excellent.
She can take on the Level 4.
It appears her activation
was successful.
If she and Walker work
together, we should be fine.
[KOMUI]
I'm not sure.
Allen's exhausted, stretched
way beyond his limits.
And Lenalee's boots,
this is first time
she's activated them.
[static]
[BOTH yell]
[LEVEL 4 groaning]
You're too weak by yourself.
But I'm not alone.
[LEVEL 4]
The girl!
[LENALEE]
Gotta get higher.
The higher the drop,
the greater speed!
I'll accelerate for more power.
[LENALEE]
These Dark Boots,
they're way different
from the previous ones.
There's no need to control them.
They respond to my
thoughts all on their own.
They don't feel like an
Equipment Type at all.
[LENALEE]
Launching!
[LEVEL 4]
Let me go!
There's no way! You're finished!
I said let me go,
you pathetic human scum!
Is it over with?
[ALLEN] Just as it appears
we've won against the Level 4,
the Akuma refuses
to be defeated,
lashing out at us
with tremendous rage.
Now, the final battle begins.
On the final episode
of D.Gray-man:
"Echoes in the Long Morning."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[LAVI]
What a day!
--[LENALEE] You said it!
--[ALLEN] Wanna grab some chow?
--That sounds great!
--Yeah!
[chuckles]
It's mine! All mine! I have just
taken control of the classroom!
[ALLEN]
Um, hey, Level 4?
School's been let
out for the day,
so you should probably leave
and go home before
the teachers find you.
I can't win.
[LENALEE, LAVI]
Hm?