The first mission for me...!
The first mission for me!
Today is my first mission,
oh the first mission for me!
Try to keep it down...
It isn't safe out here.
But I can't help it...!
This is my first official
assignment as an Exorcist!
I can't contain myself...!
Who wouldn't be overwhelmed
with the excitement?
We still have to be careful...
The forest is full
of bears and wolves.
Uh?
If you want to keep
singing, go ahead...
It'll just make us that
much easier to track.
Even so...
Let them follow us
if they want to...
No wildlife is a match for me!
They've found me!!!
Then it's a good thing they're
no match for you, isn't it?
Hi guys...
What are you doing
out here, Krory?
Hey!
Lavi...! Bookman...!
You... shouldn't
sneak up on people.
I hear Krory's been sent
out on his first mission...
I hope he does all right.
I wouldn't worry about him...
After all he's been through,
I bet he can handle anything...
Well... Almost anything.
Tell me Lavi...
Did you come here to
help me on my mission?
Komui asked me to join you.
I don't need anyone to
keep an eye on me, you know.
I'm going to a region
that's had a rash
of strange
disappearances lately...
Villagers from several towns
in the area have gone missing...
It is up to me alone
to solve this mystery.
Well, it's obvious
you can't wait.
You have no idea.
When I solve the case,
I'll be a hero!
The townsfolk will shower me
with praise and affection!
In fact, I've even started
working on my autograph!
Nice...
Words can't express my delight
in joining such a
noble profession...
It's exactly what I've been
searching for my whole life.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait up!
There's a village up ahead.
Never fear, gentle villagers!
Your hero has arrived!
That stained glass window...
It must be the reflection
we saw from a distance.
Well...
It seems the air in this village
is unnaturally calm and pure.
It is, now that you mention it.
So the village we're in now--
Is... here...
The Xs mark the towns that
have reported disappearances...
That's almost every
other town in the area...
I'm sure it's only a matter of
time until it happens here.
Yes...!
And with people
strangely vanishing,
the townsfolk must be
living in constant fear!
Perhaps not constant,
but nevertheless,
I'm here...! I'll save them!
Anything unusual, huh?
Something out of the ordinary...
It could be an event,
or even an animal...
Anything at all.
Can't help you.
Thanks anyway.
Finding clues is
harder than I thought.
Do you want to hear
something really neat?
We have a monster...!
He's at my house now!
A monster, you say?
This is where you say
we'll find the monster?
Yeah!
Ah...! Didn't expect
you back so soon.
Hi, Papa!
These people wanted to
come and see the monster.
So that's it, then...
Hey, Monster...! Come here!
Were you calling for me?
That's it...
No doubt about it.
My fangs never lie...!
And my fangs are telling me--
That's an Akuma!
Akuma?
A demon that lives
to destroy humans!
What... I am?
Who are you people?
We've been sent to help you...
We're Exorcists.
Oh, I was afraid of that.
Keep your family back...
This monster will
never kill again!
Kill...?! Not me...!
I'm innocent...!
I've never killed
anybody in my life!
Gimme a break...
Tell us what you're
planning to do...
Don't hurt me!
I'm not planning anything!
I'm just a hired farm hand...
I promise you...!
You have to believe me!
He's lying.
When I first came to this town,
the people here were scared...
They'd never seen
anyone that looked like me.
But soon... they saw
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
And they welcomed me.
Here!
After that, the villagers
gave me a home...
They taught me how good it feels
to work hard and earn a living.
I could never hurt the people
that have been so good to me.
I won't be taken in
by the lies of an Akuma!
Leave him alone!
Ow...! Stop that...!
I'm trying to stop him
from killing you guys!
Our friend here would
never do a thing like that.
Huh?
You can learn a
lot about somebody
by working along side 'em.
And this fella here is
about as decent as they come.
This thing?
Sure, he may look
like an evil monster...
But he's as much a part
of this town as I am...
And we're not gonna
let you hurt him.
Thank you, Boss...!
Thank you, everyone.
Leave it to an Akuma to
deceive an entire village.
What's wrong with you...?
Let me go!
What is it?
It's possible...
he's telling the truth.
Eliade was the same way.
I have a feeling...
...that an Akuma
with a good heart
actually could coexist
peacefully with others.
So we leave an Akuma free
to roam around the village...?
People could end up dead
because of your "feeling"!
That's true.
There's trouble!
Run...! They've wiped out Adel!
I was in Adel only yesterday
delivering another
shipment of milk,
and nothing at all seemed
out of the ordinary...
And today it's this...
Everyone in the village is gone.
Down to the last soul.
Ah... I see.
Let me guess...
An Akuma did this, right?
So... it was the
Akuma in town after all.
Seems so...
And judging by the amount of
damage that thing left behind...
It's moved up to a higher level.
If we don't do something fast...
The entire region
will be destroyed.
I will stop it...! Or my
name's not Arystar Krory.
The entire town?
I don't know for certain
if what they said was true,
but I do know that something
terrible killed those folks.
But if it is true,
then that must mean
everyone who went missing
before was killed too!
That gentle creature
is crying just like... me.
Do you know where the
Akuma was yesterday?
You just don't let up, do you?
You keep saying he's an Akuma...
But he's not...!
As a matter of fact,
he's been working in
the field with us all day!
And at night?
He stays in a little cabin
outside of the village...
The boss lets
him use it, okay...
Is there anything else?
Do you really still suspect
that precious Akuma...?
Just look at the
way he's crying...!
That poor thing
isn't our villain.
I hope you're right.
Of course I'm right...!
It seems that short of
capturing the actual Akuma,
there's nothing that
will convince you...
I'll have to find
the true killer myself.
Our town could easily be next!
Starting tonight,
every available man
will guard the village.
What we're after has taken out
whole communities before...
I don't know if we have what
it takes to stop this thing.
But... you do have that.
The stained glass window...
Come to think of it, there's
an old legend that says
that window has the power
to drive away evil spirits.
This isn't the time to rely
on old wives' tales everybody!
You're right...
The responsible thing is
to clear out the church
in case we need to use it as a
shelter when the demon comes.
Is there anything
I can do to help out?
Thank you, friend.
If only all monsters
were as wonderful as you.
Boss...
Is it okay if
I stand guard, too?
Of course...
I'll give you a post tomorrow,
but for tonight just
try to get some rest.
Thanks... I will...
Well, see you tomorrow then.
We'll be patrolling
the village...
Toma, you keep an
eye on that Akuma.
The air... It changed!
Grow...! Grow...! Grow!
This atmosphere isn't the
same as the air in the village!
Why hello there!
You scared me...
I thought you
might be the demon!
I didn't mean to scare you.
Huh...
I didn't make it.
It's that Akuma!
I promise...
I will destroy this monster.
I'm coming!
He's still close by!
Krory, no!
For all of the crimes
that you have committed...
You must die!
Very impressive...
But still no match for me...
I look forward to
draining your blood!
You?!
If we don't hurry and
get this window moved
somewhere safe, who
knows what might happen...?
Tie it tight!
So... How was it?
Ah, yeah... The Akuma...
I kept watch all night
and the monster never
left its cabin until morning...
What it was doing in
there I can only guess.
I see... and Krory?
He's still moping...
He won't forgive himself for
letting the Akuma get away.
The day before
yesterday it was here...
Yesterday it was here...
What could it be after?
Perhaps it's waiting
on more Akuma.
You could be right!
But that wouldn't
explain why this town
is the only one that
hasn't been attacked.
I wonder...
Hey...! Are you okay?
Is that what I think it is?
Innocence...
That must be what keeps
the air here so pure.
A whole gang of Akuma!
I'm not surprised...
Now that the window's broken,
there's nothing left
to keep them at bay.
Well time to get to work...
Come on!
Don't go having all the fun
Grandpa, save some for me...
Mister Monster?
I don't understand it...
He seemed to be having
so much fun working.
After these children put their
trust in you, you betrayed them!
It didn't betray them!
This is the true
nature of an Akuma!
It came to this town for one
purpose and one purpose only.
Innocence!
The power of the Innocence
formed a protective
barrier around the village.
Its effect was amplified
by the stain glass window...
Level one Akuma weren't
able to penetrate the barrier...
But Level twos had
no problem getting in...
But the Innocence
reversed its personality...
However when it stepped
outside the barrier,
it reverted back
to its true self.
It was attacking the other
villages this whole time.
You thought the Akuma
had changed its evil ways,
but it was an illusion...
Oh no.
Kids! Are you all right?
Papa!
So... He did this to us.
How could I let it
trick me like that?
Krory!
The monster I've
so strongly defended
shows its true form at last.
What is he trying to do?
I believed in you...
That good Akuma
could really exist!
That crazy fool!
I missed him!
If this is indeed
your true self...
I will show no mercy!
No... He won't make it...
Stop it!
Don't you hurt him...!
You're being a bully!
Stay back, children!
This is not the gentle
monster you've come to know!
It's an Akuma!
That's not true...!
He's Mister Monster!
Stop Mister Monster...
Why don't you just go back
to how you were before...
Remember how much fun
we had playing together?
Remember?
This happened because of you...!
If you hadn't come, Mister
Monster wouldn't be an Akuma...!
Now he's dead
and it's all your fault!
Please...! Please...!
You have to bring
Mister Monster back!
Bring... him... back!
Stop it... That's enough, now.
I don't know if our friend
was an Akuma or a monster,
but to our families,
he was never anything
but gentle and kind.
It's true...
Maybe he wasn't human...
But even so, he wasn't
half the monster you are.
You're not welcome here...
Get out of our town... Now.
Just go away!
Congratulations on completing
your first mission, Krory!
Now you know...
The job of an Exorcist
is a thankless one...
We risk our lives
making people safe,
but if praise is
what you're after--
Maybe you shouldn't
have become an Exorcist.
You're just soft...
It's not for everyone.
Becoming an Exorcist
has made me happier
than I've ever been...
Huh...
For once in my life,
I've done something
good for people...
I protected an entire village!
Sure did.
Unless I'm mistaken,
I believe we've just witnessed
the birth of another Exorcist.
In our quest to
find General Cross,
we went to see a highly
influential supporter
of the Black Order--a
woman known only as Mother.
But on the way there, we were
ambushed by a hoard of Akuma!
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The One Who Sells Souls,"
part one of two...