Exorcists...
Chosen, by God Himself...
They exist to destroy the evil
that lurks in the darkness...
an evil that brings pain
and suffering to the world.
Timcanpy! Timcanpy!
You should be
careful where you fly...
One of those cats'll eat ya.
It looks like you
could use some food.
Oh wow, thank you.
Oh, are you on a trip?
No ma'am...
I'm just on my way to
an important place.
I'm going to the
Exorcist Headquarters.
So have you heard?
Apparently a lot of people
have disappeared in there.
Well, since it was abandoned,
travelers without
money would sleep
in there before the
morning train came.
But they never make it
through the night,
only there clothes remain.
Then it's gotta
be cursed, right?
Remember what happened
there two years ago?
Come on Moa!
You're not really
going in there?
We've being flooded
with numerous complaints
about this place...
Innocent people have been
disappearing in here.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
This building's cursed!
Listen Charles...
We're going in
there no matter what.
This curse talk is rumor for
the civilians, not the police...
Now stop being a
baby and let's go.
Okay.
It looks like a tornado
came through here.
I can't believe
anyone would choose
to spend the night
in such filth.
Augh!!
What?!
Waaah!! Something's
touching my foot!
It's just a cat.
Is everything alright...?
Moa?!
Moa?
I gotcha!
Who are you?
What are you
doing in this place?
You just made a big mistake.
You're a cop?!
That's right.
And you're under arrest?
Look... I'm really sorry...!
I was just trying
to catch that cat.
I guess...
I got a little carried away
and got a hold of you instead.
It's okay...
Believe me, I'm one
of the good guys.
I honestly had no
idea this place
had such a stigma
surrounding it.
Heck I just got into town a
few hours ago on the train.
And then I ran into this
annoying little cat...
The fur ball ate something
important of mine
so I chased him...
Next thing I knew I was in here.
You think I'm making this up...?
Master said it was my
responsibility now,
and that he'd have
my head if I lost it!
Really...?
May I speak to this Master?
Uhh... Sorry...
He went missing in
India a few weeks ago.
This is all your fault!
He is just a kid.
Just hold on a sec...
I have to go get my partner.
I'll be back soon.
What's that?
Don't you go anywhere!
Hello?!
No...
Charles.
My God...
The rumor...
Could it really be true?
What... I can't breathe.
Breathe easy...
This gas is very poisonous.
This is the work of an Akuma.
An...
Akuma?
Officer!
It's about time...
She's come to.
Oh my head...
Where am I?
At the station.
Captain!
Moa's awake and
ready for questioning!
Get her in here!
That kid...! Captain I...
We know.
We're questioning the
main suspect right now.
So your name is Allen Walker.
Admit it!
You murdered him!
I told you I'm innocent!
What proof do you
have that I did it...?
All I did was save the life
of one of your officers
before she succumbed to the gas.
A witness put you at
the scene of the crime...
Why were you there?
Look at your hand...
It's all covered in blood.
No it's not...
That's its natural color.
What... What the
hell is that...?
It's glowing green
for Christ's sake!
It's not looking good
for you right now, son.
I can only imagine your
parents are very disappointed.
Excuse me, sir.
Huh?
Mister Walker was with me
the entire time
before Charles was killed.
What?!
Uh, Captain...
I just got word from the crime
scene investigators that
a number of large caliber bullet
holes were found in the wall...
According to the boy...
The only possessions he had on
him were a cat and a suitcase.
There's no evidence
to suggest the boy
had the gun on him,
much less fired it.
It's looking like
the kid's clean.
Why did you pass out...?!
Explain yourself Moa!
I'm... sorry I failed you, sir.
I can't believe you
didn't get a look
at the killers face
when you were right there.
Uhh, I think I know
who you're looking for.
Although I didn't actually
see it with my own eyes,
I know who did it...
I can help you capture
him if you'll allow me.
Your suspect is
what's called an Akuma.
They're common...
and there very
deadly to humans...
It will keep killing
until we stop it...
and it's important that you make
the first strike before
it becomes too strong.
Akuma?
This is an anti-Akuma weapon...
Now is anyone familiar
with... exorcists?
Don't worry.
I'm a clergyman whose sole
mission is to hunt Akuma.
Oh, Exorcists?
What a load of crap.
You're free to leave...
Now get out of my sight...
I'm heading back to my office.
Officer Moa...!
Mister Walker is not to leave
your sight, you got that?!
Huh?
I heard a cop was
killed in the old church.
Not just killed.
I heard he was massacred.
It sounds like the
rumors about this place
being possessed
are true after all.
I wonder what will happen next?
How did it become possessed?
I don't know the whole story,
but it had to do with
a newlywed couple
that had a horrible accident.
My precious little Akuma.
You must take innocent
life to continue evolving.
Brother...?
Marc?
I'm home...!
You feeling any better?
Welcome home, Moa.
You've come home early today.
What's the occasion?
Look Marc...
You're not eating anything
at all these days...
How do you expect
to have any strength?
I just haven't
had an appetite...
It's fine.
Don't worry...
I'll be hungry again soon.
Whatever you do,
don't stop fighting...
My sister would
want it that way.
Hey, easy with
the claws already!
Real nice...
Let me take a guess...
You were gonna try to
get to the crime scene?
Just for a second.
Absolutely not!
I'm so close.
I just hope I can find this
monster before it's too late.
So tell me.
Allen, how confident are you
that the killer is
an actual Akuma?
Huh?
This encyclopedia says
Akuma are imaginary demons
that were created by
ancient civilizations
to explain illness
and natural disasters.
You're telling me that's are
killer, some make believe demon.
I'm not buying it.
The encyclopedia is
talking about something
entirely different than
what I'm looking for.
Akuma's also the
name of a weapon.
Weapons that are
specifically created
to target mankind are the Akuma
I'm concerned with finding.
They take on the
form of humans,
so they're very
difficult to find.
Marc, are you okay?
What's wrong?
What's happening?
Oh my God.
Moa, can you hear me?
Are you hurt?
Where are we?
We're back in the church.
What's that...
Don't tell me you actually
caught the bullet!
Don't touch it!
This came from an Akuma...
Each bullet is filled with an
extremely destructive virus...
They use a defense system
where they transform
their bodies into guns.
Making them highly
effective killers.
After a bullet hits you,
it takes less than a minute
for the virus to eat
away your insides.
I couldn't save you kitty.
I'm sorry.
So then.
Tell me what happened to Marc?
Well...
Akuma take over a dead person's
body to blend in with society.
That wasn't your brother, Moa.
An Akuma had already killed him
and taken over his corpse.
So... you mean that Marc...
was already dead?
Come here!
Hey!
What in the hell are
you two doing here?!
Captain!
Ouh... My God...
What the hell?
Men...! Fire!
Your guns are useless...!
Get out of here while you can!
Oh no!
Captain...?
Oh my God...
You damn monster...!
Why did you have
to kill them...?!
Tell me!
It can't hear you...
Look...
It's not doing it
because it wants to.
It's programmed to do nothing
but seek evolution
through murder.
So you're just a mindless
killing machine?!
No...
They're living weapons who carry
around the souls of others.
These souls are
controlled by the Maker,
and are conscious to
what's happened to them.
They're left to agonize over
their sins, fully aware
of their situation but unable
to do anything about it.
All of these pent up feelings
are used as energy
for the Akuma,
allowing it to evolve
quickly and efficiently.
I can see this Akuma's soul...
Hold on...
It's a woman...
She has a strong bond with Marc.
Akuma are machines not
made of mechanical parts,
but from the sorrow experienced
by the souls they inhabit.
Everyone has a dark
side within their heart.
The Maker seeks out anyone
whose dark side has grown
due to a recent personal tragedy
and transforms them into Akuma.
Tragedy.
Now Claire, are you
and Moa still fighting?
We are.
I just don't want
her to become a cop...
I fear that doing it
just to catch the people
who killed your parents
is the wrong reason.
Claire...
Moa isn't becoming
a police officer
so she can seek revenge...
She wants to
protect us and others
from all the bad people in
the world, so we can be happy.
Have faith...
Believe me... It's okay...
Just sit down with her later.
It's our wedding day
and you look beautiful,
so let's just focus on us.
You're right...
I'll have faith.
Oh my God.
God damn you!!!
Good evening son.
Look at my newest
attractive body.
It can take a soul and
revive it back to life.
Maybe even get your Claire back
from the clutches of
your detestable God.
But in order to do so, it
needs a little of your help.
All you need do is call
out Claire's name,
and she shall return.
So all I have to do
is say her name
and she'll come back to life.
Exactly.
Come back Claire!
Marc...?
Is, is that you?
Claire!
Why'd you do it...?!
You've turned me
into an Akuma...
There's no escaping!
You did well son,
but your once bride-to-be
will do you one better.
I order you to kill this man
and wear his body as your own.
Happy Birthday...!
You are now complete.
No... It can't be...
Impossible!
There's no way that's my sister!
Sacred cross that
dwells within me...
Grant me the power to
destroy this evil darkness.
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.
I'm sorry to have to do this...
Your suffering will end
forever in just a moment.
May you rest in peace...
Claire.
Thank you.
My brother and Claire...
they're together in
heaven now, right?
Together and happy...
for sure.
I just don't understand.
He's called The
Millennium Earl...
That's the name
the Maker goes by...
He's enacted a plan that will
wipe out mankind if he succeeds.
As an Exorcist, it's my job
to put an end to his reign.
Are you ready...
let's get out of here.
I'm heading to the
Exorcist Headquarters,
commonly known
as the Black Order.
But before I can
even set foot indoors,
a man with a sword pointed at
me intends to strike me down.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The Black Order."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.