The Heart of Innocence?
Yes, though we still don't fully
understand exactly what it is.
For instance, are
there any characteristics
that can help us distinguish
it from other Innocence?
The cube doesn't say.
One possibility that we need
to consider is that someone
may have already retrieved it
and become its Accommodator.
In regards to the
Millennium Earl...
and judging by
the recent events,
it appears that he
suspected the Heart
to reside among
the upper echelon
of Accommodators
within the Order.
Which lead to
our first victim...
General Yeegar...
The resurgence of
the Clan of Noah,
and the fact that they
are appearing with
Akuma suggests that they are
strengthening their forces.
Sounds like a good assessment...
If you couple that
with the timing
of the Earl's most recent
message to the Exorcists,
I'd say we are right on track.
It makes sense,
if I had to choose
an Accommodator
that can handle the
Heart of Innocence,
a General would be the
most likely candidate.
However...
A coordinated attack
by the Clan of Noah
and Akuma would put any
General at a grave disadvantage.
At this point we have only
four General's remaining...
Klaud Nine... Socalo...
Cross... and finally, Tiedoll.
I'm assigning teams of Exorcists
to protect our Generals so
that we may defend against
the attacks that
are sure to come.
Allen, Lenalee,
listen closely...
You are to leave now...
You must General Cross
and protect him.
Are you okay?
It's just you haven't
seemed yourself lately...
Does it have anything to do with
General Yeegar passing away?
I guess...
He was
such a nice man...
He treated me like
I was his student,
like I was one of his own.
Before meeting him...
I never thought a General
was capable of generosity.
Because...
The image in my head of a
General was always
a self-centered, egotistical
sociopath who would
deal out pain and suffering
without a moments notice.
It seems like General Cross
put you through the ringer...
Does that sound about right?
Just thinking back to my days
in training makes me dizzy!
Oh no, I'm feeling faint!
Maybe you should sit
down for a sec...
Of all people, why me?
Cause you're his apprentice.
Huh?
Remember what my brother said?
As you are aware,
we have not been in contact
with General Cross in
nearly four years now...
Either he's dead,
or he's up to no good,
both of which are bad for us.
There have been numerous rumors.
If you want to know my
opinion I think he's alive...
But now I know how
to track him down...!
Thanks to you.
He's a rat in a trap
and you're the bait!
Now you're under
orders to find him.
So, the only thing
I don't understand
is why we're going to
Liverpool of all places.
It's cause of a woman...
She and Cross
were very close once,
so I thought it'd be
a good place to start.
A woman...? His girlfriend?
No... it's his sponsor.
Have you... ever met
General Cross before?
Yeah I met him briefly
at Headquarters once,
but that was a long time ago.
If that's the case,
I think it'd be best if I told
you about him beforehand.
There's some things you need to
know about what makes him tick.
I hope you enjoy your tea.
You told me once
your first encounter
with General Cross
was three years ago.
That's right,
it was three years...
It was right after I had
destroyed my father,
and then foolishly turned
him into an Akuma.
I'm so sorry...
I never meant to
bring up bad memories.
It's fine...
That wasn't the worse part.
The hard times came later.
What was so difficult
about his training?
Was he physically
abusive or something?
No not that...
The training was
the easiest part...
But Master Cross' inability
to manage his money
is what did me in.
There you are, Cross!
How you doin...?
So you think you could
take my woman's money
and get away with it unharmed.
Get up, let's have a chat.
Master Cross, hold up!
Get back here you freak!
Give me my money
or you're a dead man!
Get 'em!
Take good care of
them for me, will ya?
Huh?
Here.
Uhh... What am I supposed
to do with that?
Can't you read, kid?
It's insurance...
Now sign on the line now.
If your Master can't
pay off his debts
then his apprentice will
have to pay with his life...
If you want to give us
any trouble you'll end up
at the bottom of the
Seine, so just try me.
Help...! Someone help me!!!
Hey, get back here you brat!
I managed to escape,
but it wasn't the last time...
Master Cross accumulated debts
across all of Europe,
one after another.
Hey little guy...!
Take a break...!
I don't want you
wearing yourself out now.
Thank you...! But I think
I'll save it for later
after I get some more work done.
Well don't kill yourself.
After working off
Master Cross's debts,
I'd only take home a
fraction of what I earned.
You worked all day long
and this is all you
have to show for it...?
You're more pathetic
than I thought.
Wait... Master Cross...
Try making some more money kid.
I will one day...
Ugh... I can't even tell you
how many times I wanted
to lash out at him.
But of course when all
was said and done...
I continued to work
myself to the bone
in order to pay off the
rest of what he owed.
At one point I was working
on a fishing boat in
the Mediterranean Sea.
Another time I was hauling cargo
across the Egyptian desert,
and nearly got myself
killed in the process.
And then we ended up in Kenya.
Allen, yeah... I want
to see one of those lions...
Go get one for me.
I still can't believe
I survived that day.
I remember thinking that
if I continued to
do these jobs...
I wasn't going to see
my next birthday.
So in order to make enough
money to live on my own...
I learned how to gamble.
Royal straight flush.
I originally started
playing cards
so I could rehabilitate
my paralyzed left hand.
But when you're
putting your life
on the line in dirty saloons,
your skills can advance quickly.
Soon enough I had mastered
a slew of cheats
and couldn't lose.
Now I can't touch a deck of
cards without winning money.
Do you not believe me?
No... I believe you Allen!
Okay... That was a bit creepy...
But my new talent
put me in a dilemma...
Once Master realized
how much money
I could bring
in gambling...
...his spending and
partying skyrocketed.
I started to believe
I would be a slave
to my Master for
the rest of my life,
and it turned me into
a really mean person...
But Allen, that's how
anyone would react...
Besides, things would
have been a lot better
if you had a friend
that you could talk to.
Something wrong...?
Did I just bring up another
bad memory from your past?
I did have a friend...
That's crazy, huh...?
I'd finally found someone...
He was somebody
I could confide in
and depend on and honestly
call my best friend.
Narain was his name.
He was my age...
...and he changed
my life forever...
Hey Allen...
What happened to you?
I had to clean a bunch
of chimneys today
and I ended up
falling off of the roof...
I twisted my ankle.
Way to go...
Show it to me.
Ah, take it easy.
That hurt!
Well the good news is
your bone isn't broken.
Don't be so rough Narain,
my ankle really hurts...
A little pain will
do you some good.
I met him while
I was working in India...
Right after we moved
there from Africa...
Master ended up living
in a palace that belonged
to the Maharaja,
who ruled the land.
Inside the palace lived a widow
that went by the name Urmina...
She and Master Cross
were... well, you know...
Lovers?!
Geez... Keep it down.
I'm sorry,
but did he really do that
with a Maharaja's widow?
Yeah...
Honestly I don't know
how it's even possible,
but Master's very
good with the ladies.
While Master was
getting to know Urmina,
I got to know Narain...
I immediately noticed
how smart he was.
He wanted to become a
doctor when he grew up.
Any time he wasn't working,
he would immerse himself
in advanced medical books,
studying so he could
one day attain his dream.
He had an older
sister named Miena...
She worked as Urmina's servant.
Miena's dream was to
someday become a dancer,
so every chance she got she
would twirl through the palace,
dreaming of being
on stage in London.
Whenever I saw those two...
they would really help me see my
own situation in a better light.
So they encouraged you.
Yes, definitely.
Even though they were young,
they were so positive...
They both believed
deep down in their hearts
that better times were waiting
for them in the future.
Unfortunately... the
future they dreamed of,
never became a reality.
I had been working in
India for six months,
when it happened.
At the local saloon,
I used money
that I had earned
from several of my jobs
to win a huge pot in one
of the poker games...
Ahh...
As usual,
Master took every penny
I had won that night.
Master how much
longer are you going
to make me keep doing this...?
Let's not forget that it was you
who asked me to
become an Exorcist.
Yet here we are
over a year later
and I still haven't
trained for one minute.
I see.
You think you're ready
for training huh?
In all my travels around
the world with Master...
I had encountered Akuma
on numerous occasions...
But I had never
actually fought one.
Here's your chance, kiddo.
Huh?
How bout you show
me what you've got...
Now?
What...? This is impossible...
Help me!
He's... crazy...
Master Cross, please help me...!
There's no way I can
take on that many!
You're not gonna get very
far fighting empty-handed.
Lucky for you, there's
an Anti-Akuma weapon
inside that body of yours.
Maybe you should
try using it, yes?
An Anti-Akuma weapon?
Of course!
Nothing happened...!
What's wrong with it?
That's creepy...
I guess this is it!
I'm gonna die in my
first training session!
You're pathetic...!
For punishment you
must earn twice as much
from here on out...
Starting tomorrow...
After that incident...
I was down in the
dumps once again.
So I decided to visit Narain in
the hopes that he'd cheer me up,
he was always good at that.
It's my sister...
She went into town...
to buy a book for me.
A monster appeared... and
everyone started to panic...
then the building
collapsed... on top of her.
I've looked through all my books
and I can't find anything
about how I can revive her...
I've read so many
pages about medicine,
and there's nothing
I can do for her...!
My sister's never coming back!
Hey Narain...
I brought this... for Meina.
Why thank you Allen...
Thanks a lot.
No... You can't be...
It's true... He is an Akuma.
I became concerned when
you told me he was grieving
over the unfortunate
loss of his sister.
Just as I thought,
the Millennium Earl paid
him a visit after all.
Wait, the Millennium Earl?
The Earl prey's on people
who are weak with sorrow
and turns them into Akuma.
Meina!!!
New mourning gives
birth to new Akuma...
In order to break that chain
it is our duty as Exorcists
to destroy every Akuma
that roams the Earth.
Now do it, Allen!
Destroy the Akuma
that stands before you!
What...? Impossible!
I can't do that!
It's Narain, I...
He's my friend!
I can't kill him...!I won't!
Your friend is already dead...
He's an Akuma that's
wearing Narain's skin.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Allen, you have to destroy it!
Stop...! Don't run.
It's your duty to break the
chain of sorrow Allen, do it.
Sorrow?
The soul is crying...
It's... Miena.
Even though I passed away,
you should have continued
to live your life,
so you could work towards your
dream of becoming a doctor...
Why didn't you go after
your dream... Narain?
All Akuma are grieving...
They feel horrible for
allowing themselves
to be turned into weapons
and are crying for help.
The only way I can alleviate
their pain and purify it,
is by destroying the Akuma
and releasing their soul.
I have no other choice.
Bring forth salvation... to
this tormented Akuma's soul!
Rest in peace... Miena.
Thank you so much... Allen.
Miena... And Narain.
How was it...?
Tell me exactly how it felt
to destroy an Akuma
for the first time.
It was hard... so hard.
Because... my friends...
...still aren't
coming back to me!
That's something you're
gonna have to get used to,
because if you can't,
then the life of an
Exorcist is not for you.
Good work today...
Considering it was
your first time,
you did exceptionally well.
That was two years ago.
And so Master continued to
throw me into the heat
of battle every time an Akuma
would appear before us...
I welcomed the experience.
I guess you weren't kidding...
That's a crazy story...
Much crazier than
I thought it'd be...
For all of General
Cross' flaws though...
He sounds interesting...
Now you know what
I was talking about...
My Master's crazier than a...
He sounds amazing!
Say what?!
I didn't understand
everything...
Especially the part
about the Akuma
or whatever you
call those things,
but there's one thing
I know for sure...!
This Master of yours
is a commendable man!
Most people can only dream of
having such a
positive influence!
Your story really
touches my heart...!
What a charming man
this Master Cross is!
Oh, I'd love to meet him!
What...? My story...
touched you...?
Wait, which part?!
The whole thing!
Hold on!
My Master's a maniac...!
How can you find that endearing?
Now now...
Did you ever think that
General Cross is strict
with you because
he cares about you?
What...? You too Lenalee...?!
I don't get it...
Why are women so easily swayed
by guys like Master?
I guess it's true
that women really do
like men who have a bad side?
The thing with Master is
he's not just bad, he's evil!
So why do women constantly
fawn all over him...?!!!
Oh, forget it! I'll never
understand women!
I'm clueless! There, I said it!
Arystar Krory is
now an Exorcist...
His orders take him to a village
where he encounters
a formidable Akuma,
the likes of which he
has never seen before.
On the next episode of
D. Gray-man: "Exorcist Krory."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.