Wait... Where are all the ships?
Gone...
They only come
every other day now,
so you'll have to
wait 'til tomorrow.
I heard there were
passenger ships
in and out of here every day.
There aren't enough
ships for all that anymore.
Not since so many
of them have been
sinking like stones
in the waters near here.
They're sinking...?
But what's causing it?
Its pirates, that's what!
You know it's pirates...!
We told you so!
Pirates?
You brats and your stories...!
Keep telling lies like that and
it'll come back to haunt ya!
I don't really care if you
believe me or not...!
Pirates are
responsible for this!
You punks...
That's enough!
One of these days
I'm finally gonna get
my hands on those
lying little kids.
There aren't any real pirates?
Our coral reefs do more
damage than any pirates...
And there are lots
of rocks that are tough
for even the most
experienced sailors
to navigate around,
even in daylight.
Of course at night
it's nearly impossible.
No one who's crashed
there has ever survived.
But those kids and
their imaginations.
I'm in a bit of a hurry,
aren't there any
ships available today?
It's like I told ya...
Ships come every other day.
Well, I guess...
I'm staying here tonight.
Sure, you can find a room.
Matter of fact, I've got
one available right here...
I'll let you have it for cheap.
I'll take it. Thanks a lot.
Guest rooms are upstairs...
They're all empty,
so take your pick.
Fruit ahoy! Charge!
Watch who you're
messing with, old man!
I told you that food
is for paying customers!
Your stupid rules don't
apply to pirates like us!
Pirates, huh...?
You don't look like any
pirates I've seen before.
Yeah, well I bet
you've never even seen
a pirate at all,
you land lubber.
Now!
We'll get you for this!
Sorry sir...
Don't those kids
ever take a day off?
Doubtful...
So whose kids are they?
The leader's mine.
The rest follow him around
because he's loud
and they're dumb.
They go around calling
themselves pirates
just to get under
their parents' skin...
A typical rebellious
phase, you know.
Let's hope so...
Three hundred twenty...!
Three hundred twenty-one...
Three hundred twenty-two...
Three hundred twenty-three...
I hope I can find Master soon.
Ow!
That stings!
I know that Archie...
But it's good for
treating bruises.
I thought this time we'd be able
to steal some food
from my dad for sure.
The problem is we don't have
enough members to be scary.
Your dad wouldn't act so
tough if we had another pirate!
Another pirate, huh?
Yeah, but they can't be
any younger than we are...!
We're marauding pirates,
not babysitters.
And they can't
be an adult either,
or else they won't do
whatever we tell 'em to.
It has to be someone
that can hold
their own in a
battle with the enemy.
And a boy 'cause
girls can't be pirates.
Sure...
But where can we find
somebody like that?
I've got an idea...
What about that guy?
Four hundred five...
Four hundred six...
He isn't younger than us.
And he's not old, either.
Looks pretty strong to me!
Definitely a guy.
Four hundred and eleven...
Four hundred and twelve...
Four hundred and thirteen...
Four hundred and fourteen...
Four hundred and fifteen...
Four hundred and sixteen...
Hey, Tim...! Where'd you go?
You looking for this?
Timcanpy...
If this is a joke,
it isn't very funny.
Swirling Current Arch!
Bob...! The Hurricane!
Call me Chitta the Belly!
Calculator Dan!
And I'm Eagle-Eye Eric!
Together we are
the Abochidae Pirates!
You will fear our wrath!
Abochidae...?
They combined the first
sound in each of their names...
Wow.
And what's your name, huh?
Allen.
Congratulations, Allen...!
You've been selected
as a candidate
to potentially join the
dreaded Abochidae Pirates!
Isn't that awesome?!
A candidate for a pirate crew?
If you prove yourself worthy
by passing a series of tests,
we'll allow you
to join our ranks.
Lucky!
Well...
I appreciate the offer
but I think I'll have to pass.
If you ever want to see
your little buddy again,
then I think you might
want to reconsider.
I'm sorry, but--
Huh?
He's gone!
It's just that I'm not in the
mood for games right now.
May I please have Tim back...
Bob catch...
I got it! I got it!
Tough luck, buddy...!
If you think you can
outrun Bob the Hurricane,
you've got another thing coming!
And if I can outrun you?
This guy's unbelievable!
Nobody in town
can keep up with me!
I am asking nicely you know!
Chitta! Catch!
Got it...
Never fear!
Chitta the Belly
to the rescue...!
If you want your
little friend back,
you're gonna have to beat
me in an eating contest!
Ready... set, go!
Good luck...!
I've never lost
once in my whole--
If there's nothing else,
can I have Tim back?
You cheated!
Dan!
Calculator Dan...!
If you can come up with the
answer to this math problem
before I can, I promise you
can have your friend back.
Let's see here...
58 plus 25, carry the
three, multiply the...
The answer's 83.
No way...! But...!
Eric!
It's my turn now...!
Whichever one of us can
make the ugliest face
can keep this thing...
Okay.
You win...! Archie!
Congratulations on
making it this far.
I didn't realize
I was doing anything.
But you're not a
member just yet...
You still have to prove yourself
in one final
challenge against me...
Whoever can swim to that
rock first is the winner.
Ready... go!
Might as well keep
playing along...
Here we go...
Beat this!
What? But how?!
It's about time I settled this.
No!
Oh no... Look out...
Arch!
Archie!
I'm all right.
Maybe I shouldn't
have done that.
No one's ever beat Swirling
Current Archie before!
I didn't beat him...
Arch lost to me on purpose.
Huh?!
Wha--?!
To test my bravery,
he pretended to drown to
see if I'd try to save him.
Of course...
If he really wanted to race
me I wouldn't stand a chance.
Yeah! I planned the whole thing!
That is so cool!
I knew it!
Allen Walker...
Welcome to the
Abochidae Pirates.
Me?
Let's hear it for
our new member!
But... I wasn't trying to join!
Yeah...! Cool!
Now I don't want you
to start thinkin'
I owe you or anything...
I had an off day,
it happens to everybody...
But the next time we race
it'll be the real deal!
Uh... huh...
Pretty incredible, isn't it?
Yeah...! It's definitely
a meal for a working man!
A working man...?
Yeah, that's a laugh...
Cooking and cleaning
doesn't sound much
like a man's work to me!
What'd you just say?!
You used to be a sailor...!
Now you're just a shopkeeper!
Sit down and finish your food!
I lost my appetite.
What was that?
It's none of your business.
The kid seems to have
taken a liking to you...
I hope he's not too
much of a bother...
No... Not at all.
It's okay...
He gets his crudeness
from his old man.
I'm sorry about that...
Sorry you've got to put up with
all that pirate
nonsense of his...
If only his mother
were still alive,
maybe he wouldn't have turned
out so rough around the edges.
Arch mentioned that
you used to be a sailor?
Oh, yeah...
I've taken fish out of every
ocean on the face of the planet!
Every day I put my life on
the line to bring in a catch...
And I loved every minute of it.
If you loved it
then why did you stop?
It wasn't an easy
choice for me to make.
I miss the sea but
my life's on land, now.
A single father
and his only son...
Maybe that's the reason
Jid decided to stop sailing.
You're late!
This cave is our top-secret
pirate headquarters.
Archie... Allen...
You came.
We're building a ship...
And once we finally get it
finished we'll be unstoppable!
We're gonna sail
right into the ocean!
And we'll kill every one
of those stinkin' pirates!
What pirates?
There really are
pirates around here;
we saw 'em with our own eyes!
One night we all
gathered right here
in this cave to
watch the ships come in.
From here you can see
the ships coming down
the channel way
before anybody else can.
Most ships come in
sometime in the afternoon...
But this one had been
riding out a storm,
so it didn't make it back
until it was really late.
All of a sudden
the wind picked up.
We ran back to town and told
every grown-up we could find.
Because we're kids they thought
we made the whole thing up!
That's why we're gonna go out
and find the pirates ourselves.
We'll show everybody we were
right and they were wrong!
They're really
serious about this.
We're the only ones
that can stop them.
It's up to us
to rescue the town!
But we can't do it
without your help!
Please, Allen!
If these kids are right...
But still--
Fighting pirates is
a pretty big job,
but your dad's an
experienced sailor...
Maybe he'll have a few ideas.
Don't talk about my old man!
Archie...
He used to be a sailor,
but he gave up!
If you think we should
ask that quitter for help,
maybe you don't
belong here...! Get out!
Archie!
Out!
If you're ever in the
neighborhood again,
feel free to stop on by.
I will.
I apologize again about Arch...
For him and his friends to
cause you all that trouble,
then not even come
to see you off...
I didn't turn out to
be much of a pirate.
What?
I don't know, just
rambling I guess, sorry...
It's finished...!
Those pirates don't stand
a chance against us now!
All right!
Come on, you guys...
Let's go!
Yeah!
Hi, it's Allen.
I know I'm already
running a day behind,
but there should be
another ship along any minute.
I'm relieved you
called to check in with me.
Several ships have reportedly
gone missing in that area...
There are so many similar cases
it could hardly
be a coincidence.
A deluxe passenger ship went
missing yesterday, in fact.
A passenger ship...?
It couldn't have been--
Hey...! You kids!
Come back here...
Jid?
Arch!
Hey, Archie...
Your dad looks even
madder than usual.
Let the old man be
as mad as he wants.
See if I care.
Oh no... There's an
Akuma on board that ship!
What's that?
That's the same
pirate ship from before!
What do we do?
We destroy them, that's what!
Quick, I need a boat!
Your son and his friends
are in grave danger!
Archie?
That passenger ship
is under enemy fire!
We need a boat!
What was that?
It's a reef...
We've run aground
and now we're sitting
ducks for those pirates!
Die, die, die!
This is bad...
This is really bad!
We'll use our secret weapon!
Wait for it... Fire!
Yeah...! That oughta show him!
That actually kinda scared me...
Take that!
Allen!
Old man?
What's going on with your hand?
I'll explain everything later...
Right now I need
you to get these kids
to safety while
I take care of that ship.
An Exorcist, huh?
So you're the one who's been
attacking all those ships!
Guilty as charged!
It's a great way to kill
a lot of people at once
and move up another level!
Not if I can do
anything about it!
Where is it...?
Where's the Akuma?
Is it on the deck...?
Wait, no...!
The entire ship is an Akuma?
Took you long enough!
Ah, that was close...!
Try this on for size!
Fire!
Not bad...!
But take that...! And that!
Hurry!
We have to protect a
fellow pirate in danger!
I'm coming, boy!
Dad...! No!
Old man...
Arch!
Dad! Please don't die!
I'm not gonna die...
Not while you still need
me to take care of you.
I tried to care
for your mother also.
But by the time we
realized she was sick,
it was too late.
When she died, I got
scared I might lose
my little boy,
so I quit sailing.
I promised myself that day,
I'd be by your side until
you were a grown man...
To guide and protect you...
Like your mom would have wanted.
Old man...
I had no idea you gave up
sailing because of me.
When you gave me this
telescope for my birthday,
all I wanted was to grow up
and be a sailor just
like my old man was.
Then all of a sudden you quit.
Because you said
you were scared...
I never felt so
betrayed in my life.
But the only reason you quit was
so you could stay
and protect me...
I'm sorry.
Archie!
Allen!
Aw, what's the matter?
Trouble keeping up?
I can't keep this
up much longer...
I've got to attack the
Akuma ship directly!
Come on you guys, one
of our own is in trouble!
I'm in.
For family!
For our friends!
To save the town from evil!
A ship's weakest
point is it's bridge...
See if you can hit it!
No problem!
And fire!
You again!
A smoke bomb, huh?
You'll have to do a lot better
than that if you want to a--
Aw, crap!
It took three days to repair...
But she's finally ready to sail.
Allen!
Hey!
Jid has finally taken
up sailing again...
And he's got five
young apprentices.
I guess there's only
one thing left to do...
Meet up with Lenalee...
And look for
my master, of course.
After entering
"The Forest of No Return,"
Kanda finds an
eerie little village,
completely hidden
from the outside world.
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"The Village Where
a Witch Lives."
Part one of two...
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!