--[blades slicing]
--[FO, ALLEN grunting]
[ALLEN groaning]
[grunts]
[ALLEN grunting]
Get ready! Ah!
[LO FWA snores]
Oh my gosh. Walker...
[FO yells]
[LI KEI]
Lo Fwa? Hey!
[sighs]
Out like a light.
I guess she's havin' a really
nice dream right now.
Looks like it.
[BOTH yelling]
[gasps] Walker?
[ALLEN groans]
--[LO FWA yelps]
--[SHIFU, LI KEI gasp]
Hey, what's your deal?
Don't wimp out on me, Walker!
[panting]
[FO growls]
[ALLEN gasping]
[FO yelling]
[FO]
Huh?
Nice one!
[LO FWA]
Way to go!
[ALLEN grunting]
There ya go,
keep up the good work!
Great, it turned into fog again.
I'm not done!
Let's keep fighting!
That's the spirit.
[FO laughs]
[ALLEN grunts]
[BAK]
That's enough.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[ALL]
Uh?
[BAK] It's been 20 hours since
you started this fight.
You're done for the day.
What? No wait, I still
have some energy left!
I can't stop!
[BAK]
You won't get anywhere
unless you rest up once
in a while, Walker.
Are we clear?
[ALLEN grunts]
Yes, sir.
[SHIFU]
This is the data we gathered
when you started training.
The point where you first
employed your plan
to force your Innocence out
through fear of death--is here.
But the timeline doesn't
show any change
in your activation
time after that.
Since you weren't
getting results,
you and Fo began to make changes
to your training routine.
This graph shows
the data from that.
You tried training at
different times of day,
even shortening and
lengthening your battles.
You adjusted several
different variables,
but after today's 20-hour
training session,
we still aren't seeing
a difference in output.
So what could possibly
be the problem here?
I mean, do you have any idea
what could be missing, Shifu?
Well... That's a difficult
question to answer,
since there's never been
a case quite like this.
Think about it, we're trying
to activate an Innocence
that's already been destroyed.
I'm not sure that's
even possible.
Are you okay?
Huh? Oh, me?
Yeah. I guess I kinda
blew it today, didn't I?
My bad, guys.
Okay! I'll just have to try
extra hard tomorrow! Yeah!
Anyway. I'd better be
getting back to my room now.
See ya.
He's pushin' himself
really hard.
Yeah, I suppose he's more upset
about this situation
than any of us are.
Poor Walker.
We're very concerned
about all of this.
I agree.
What if our base comes under
attack because of that boy?
[BOTH] Are you gentlemen
sure it's necessary
for Walker to be staying
at the Asian Branch?
Have you considered transferring
him to headquarters?
They have better facilities
and more personnel there.
[WONG] But what if he
was spotted by Akuma
or the Noahs during transport?
As it stands, he's a
normal human being.
He wouldn't have any
way to protect himself.
Well, we'll have to
take our chances.
He's an Exorcist who
can't use Innocence.
Doesn't that mean he's of
no use to the Black Order?
You... You'd best
hold your tongue!
I understand what you're
trying to express here.
That said, Walker isn't
useless by any means.
As you know, the number of
Exorcists is steadily declining.
Each one we have is
much too valuable
to let go, Walker included.
In fact, he's a
crucial asset to us.
I assure you that the
Asian Branch, actually,
the Order as a whole cannot
afford to lose him.
If you feel that
strongly about it,
then it seems we have no choice.
[WONG]
The nerve.
To think they'd even suggest
something like that.
[BAK]
I'm sure they're afraid too.
The Noahs have been relentless
in their pursuit of Walker.
The most troubling part is,
they're not trying to kill Allen
Walker because he's an Exorcist
or because of his Innocence.
But, because of his connection
to a certain someone.
I tried asking Walker
about that connection,
but he didn't know who it was.
That's exactly why we can't
let him set foot outside
until the situation is resolved
and his weapon is recovered.
He'll be safe at the Asian
Branch until then.
[BAK] Luckily that deity
my grandfather made
is sealing the entrance
with a protective barrier.
[ALLEN grunting]
[yawns]
We're gonna start
tomorrow's training
at 12 o'clock sharp, okay?
[ALLEN]
I wish we could start sooner.
[ALLEN grunting]
[ALLEN] Come on. I have to
hurry back to my friends.
I have to get my
Innocence back...
...and fast!
[wood splitting]
[panting]
Damn. What's taking me so long?
I should be...
[BRANCH MEMBER B] I still can't
say I support the decision
regarding Allen Walker.
[ALLEN]
Uh?
[BRANCH MEMBER B]
An Exorcist who can't
activate his Innocence.
How much good could he
be to the Asian Branch?
[BRANCH MEMBER A]
Give it a rest.
The Chief already
made the call, right?
No helping it.
Look at it this way,
this is even more of a
problem for the Chief.
With Walker showing
no improvement,
this has got to be a
tough choice for him.
[ALLEN exhales]
[ALLEN grunts]
[FO] We're just gonna
train for an hour today.
It's not much, but we'll
make it count, I promise.
Are you listening?!
[gasps] Uh. Yeah!
[FO yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[ALLEN groaning]
[FO]
Wow, okay.
[FO yells]
[ALLEN grunting]
[BRANCH MEMBER A] This is even
more of a problem for the Chief.
With Walker showing
no improvement,
this has got to be a
tough choice for him.
[ALLEN]
I'm causing Bak so much trouble.
[FO yells]
[ALLEN grunting]
[ALLEN]
Everyone's counting on me.
[ALLEN] I have to bring
back my Innocence.
I have to keep fighting!
Come on, hurry!
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[FO growls]
Idiot!
--What's wrong with you?!
--[ALLEN groans]
Oh, no! Walker!
Hey, stay back!
You'll get hurt!
Stop wasting time!
What's your deal?!
Please, Fo!
He's not feeling well.
Give him a break, okay?
[FO]
Ugh, do I look like I care?
Why aren't you giving
it your best?!
This... is my best.
Don't you lie to me, Walker!
Jeez, what is it gonna take?
I'm starting to think you don't
even want to make this happen!
Get your head in the game
before it's too late, kid.
What, do you have something more
important to worry about?
I know, you're scared,
aren't you?
You make me sick,
you little baby!
What makes that stupid Bak
think a short stack like you
could revive your Innocence?!
[ALLEN yells]
Uh-oh, you broke Walker!
What are you freakin' out about?
This is all your fault!
Would you please calm down?
[ALLEN] I don't know what's
wrong with me either.
[BOTH]
Mm?
[ALLEN] I mean, do you think
I want to be stuck here,
doing nothing?
I don't know what to do!
I'm so lost...
Ugh. Dammit!
How long...?
How long do I have to
keep doing this?
[ALLEN grunts]
What's the matter?
I thought you were supposed
to be training right now.
Forget him. He's a loser.
Did something happen?
He's always keeping his
problems to himself.
Would it kill him to
ask for some help?
He doesn't even care how
worried I am about him!
I'm sick of that jerk.
Listen, no matter what you say,
I'm not gonna babysit that
little wuss anymore.
Are you trying to quit
training with Walker?
You heard me.
Who cares about him?
Just let him die.
[chair legs scraping]
[BAK]
Hm...
If you say so. You're a deity.
It's not like there's any way
I can stop you, right?
I guess it was just
too difficult...
All right, let's give
up on Walker then.
Huh?
Actually, if you're not
gonna work with him,
then there's no reason for him
to stay in the Asian Branch.
[FO]
H-Hey!
That's right!
I'd better take those
other guys' advice
and have him sent back
to headquarters!
Now... Now wait just a second!
I know he kinda sucks
at this and everything,
but don't you think sending
him away is too harsh?
Perhaps, but what
else can we do?
I told you. The kid's
got a lot on his mind.
You can't blame him for
being a little distracted!
Oh, yeah?
Someone's in tune with
Walker all of a sudden.
It's all over his face,
any fool can tell!
Anyway, I'm sure we'll
see some improvement.
He just needs some time
to clear his head!
Okay? Trust me!
You're not backing down.
All right, if it's that
important to you,
I say we keep working with
him to the bitter end!
Uh!
Uh. Wait, that face...
I'm just so touched by you
standing up for Walker!
[gasps] Stupid Bak!
--[crash]
--[BAK groans]
Why would I stand up for a
pathetic bean sprout like him?
You're an expert at that, sir.
Well, we can't have them
fighting, can we?
Would you like me to
help you with that?
Yes, please do.
No way! I don't care about him!
[FO]
Dammit!
[phone ringing]
[KOMUI]
Hey! It's been a while!
Komui? [growls]
[KOMUI] I've been wondering
what's going on over there!
So, I thought I'd
give you a ring.
[REEVER] Hey, Chief, could you
please stop slacking off?
[WONG exhales]
[BAK clears throat] Well, I
don't have anything to report.
The situation with Walker
isn't looking too good.
[KOMUI] I see. So why can't
he use his Innocence?
[BAK] If we knew that,
it would be easy.
One thing's for certain though,
forcing it out by backing him
into a corner isn't working.
See, we were thinking maybe
now that he's a human,
we could trigger his
survival instincts
and get him to accelerate
his evolution that way.
It seemed like a solid strategy.
But it looks like we're
starting to hit a wall.
Basically, we discovered that
Walker being placed in a crisis,
and activating his Innocence,
don't really go hand
in hand at all.
I see.
[BAK]
What now?
Well, survival is one thing,
but it's much more
complex than that.
I think there may be some
other factors involved.
[BAK]
Other factors. Like what?
Not sure. Although, I
can venture one guess.
You may not have
experienced this,
but Innocence has its own will.
I have.
Back when Walker was rescued
from the brink of death.
I thought that
might be the case.
[KOMUI]
If that's what's going on here,
the Innocence could be
longing for something.
[BAK]
Hm.
If he wants to
activate his power,
then he'll need to find
out what that is.
I think it's something Allen's
longing for at the same time.
I hope that helps.
Something that the
Innocence wants,
that Walker's looking for too.
[sighs]
[ALLEN]
What am I doing?
I should never have blown
up at Fo like that.
She was so mad,
she probably won't want
to train with me anymore.
Uh.
[ALLEN] What if I'm giving
this all I've got,
and it turns out to
be for nothing?
Do I even remember how to
activate my Innocence now?
It's weird, I can't even
recall what it felt like
to have my left arm anymore.
[ALLEN grunts]
Things are pretty dark.
Huh?
--Hello there, Walker.
--[ALLEN screams]
O-Oh! Hi, Lo Fwa!
Where'd you come from?
[LO FWA] I brought a light.
You said it was dark, so...
Oh. That's not really
what I meant, but...
[LO FWA]
Here.
[ALLEN]
Uh, thanks, I guess.
[LO FWA] So, it seems pretty
tough, getting your arm back.
I dunno. It could be worse,
right? I'm kinda pathetic.
[LO FWA] That's not true at all!
You're working very hard.
[ALLEN] Yeah, but if nothing
ever comes of it,
what's the point?
[LO FWA] Nothing? You've
already gained something.
Huh?
[LO FWA]
Well, you made some friends,
and then the Noahs
came after you
because they thought your
Innocence might be the Heart.
People died, you saw a Fallen
one, you lost your weapon.
Didn't those things make you
want to protect your comrades?
You're determined to
stop the Noahs, right?
I'm sure the burden of
the lives you couldn't save
is making you feel like
you have to fight as hard
as you possibly can.
Maybe harder than you can.
I think what's driving you
more than anything now,
is the kindness in your heart.
And yet, even though it may come
from wanting to be kind,
your determination to fight
them has gotten so powerful.
Maybe it's starting
to overshadow
that precious feeling.
The one that's been there
from the beginning.
You don't fight for
the sake of fighting.
And you certainly don't live
for the sake of fighting.
The reason you feel
so compelled to fight,
is because you have something
important to protect.
Something important, huh?
That's right.
Do you mean...?
[LO FWA]
Heh.
What's happening?
Wh-Wh-Why are there two of me?!
A-And why is one of me
flirting with Walker?!
[ALLEN]
Uh?
[LI KEI] Uh, Lo Fwa?
What's the matter?
Oh, dear.
[FO growls]
And I was so close, too.
[ALLEN]
Uh!
What?! It was Fo?!
[LI KEI, LO FWA scream]
That's right, I forgot.
She can transform
into other people.
I hear she likes to play
pranks on the Chief.
[LI KEI] Okay, but why was
she posing as Lo Fwa?
[FO grunts] Don't take it
the wrong way. Got that?
Uh...?
I... I didn't come here to
whisper sweet nothings to you!
I'm still pissed off
at you about earlier!
Don't go gettin' all excited!
[FO] Man, that kid's
a pain in the ass! Ugh!
[ALLEN]
Thank you, Fo.
For the light.
[FO] We'll train some more
after you rest up.
[ALLEN]
Sure.
And you'd better not
impersonate me anymore!
So... What was she
talking to you about?
She actually taught me
something really wise.
[SHIFU]
Hm?
[ALLEN]
You're right, Fo.
I do have something precious,
even though I've
lost sight of it.
And that's the reason
why I fight.
Because... I have to protect
what's important to me.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
What is it, Tyki, my boy?
Uh, your boy?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
What?
Ah! Nothing!
Anyway, about this guy.
Are you sure we have
the right information?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Course we do.
If the Prisoner of the List Cell
says that he's still alive,
then trust me, he's still alive.
[MILLENNIUM EARL] You mustn't
underestimate Innocence.
[TYKI]
Huh?
[MILLENNIUM EARL] It's an evil
force that seeks to destroy us.
It'll stop at nothing to do so.
[sighs]
Hey you. Come out, would ya?
I need you to use the box
and go to China right away.
With this...
Yes, sir.
I have the name of your target.
[ALLEN] Lenalee and the others
make their way to Edo,
careful not to run into
any trouble on the way.
But during the journey,
something strange
happens to the Akuma.
On the next D.Gray-Man :
"Heading to Edo."
Hey Kanda, are you sure you
don't want a bite of this cake?
No way, I can't eat sweet stuff.
[ALLEN]
Hm?
More for me then.
Fine.
Come on now...
Stop it!
[yelping]