I gotta combo one...
a combo two...
and a combo three, ready to go!
Alright...
Keep them orders rolling in now!
Hey there...
You... must be the new guy...
Oh my God, you're such
a little cutie patootie...
How do you do, sir?
My name is Allen Walker!
Woah, everybody check out
the manners on this one...
What a gentleman...
So, Allen Walker,
are you hungry?
Anything you want.
Absolutely anything I want...?
Well, okay!
Then I'll have potatoes gratin,
fries and rice pilaf...
Mabo tofu, beef stew, meat pies,
carpaccio and fried rice...
Oh, Fried chicken,
a salad, some scones,
korean barbeque,
tom kha soup and white rice.
And for dessert I'll have mango
and sticky rice with an
order of mitarashi-dango...
Oh, make that twenty of 'em!
Uhh, are you sure
you can eat all this?
What? I dare you
to say that again!
Come on, Bazu. Take it easy.
Wait a minute, is that...?
Prepare to be slaughtered...
by the mighty Mugen!
You people are
such an annoyance.
I'm minding my own business...
attempting to enjoy a nice meal
before I leave on
my next assignment...
and all I hear behind
me is whining.
You bastard...
You like disrespecting men
who've fallen in
the line of duty?
We risk our lives for
your kind every day.
And yet you have the nerve
to sit there and judge me...
simply for honoring
a great Finder...?
You smug little... sonuvabitch!
So sorry we ruined your meal!!!
You Finders are so
self-important.
The only thing you're capable
of doing is assisting us.
You all failed to
become Exorcists
and resorted to
finding instead.
That's why Innocence
chose me and none of you.
You're easily replaceable,
so if the idea of dying scares
you then I suggest you leave...
Got it?!
Stop it now!
I don't mean to get involved,
but I'm not going to stand
by and let this happen--
we're all on the same side.
Why don't you just
walk away, short-stack.
Short-stack...?
The name's Allen.
Sorry but you have to
survive at least a month
before I make
note of your name...
The turnover rate is high,
especialy with these guys .
Sadly, they all drop like flies.
You really need to learn
to watch your mouth.
And you need to keep
that cursed hand off me.
You'll be dead within a year...
Trust me... you're weak...
We'll see about that.
Hey, Reever. Check this out.
Great... Just what I needed.
Kanda!
Allen!
Get to over to the
Command Room now...
Your missions are up.
Chief... Chief...
Hey, Chief, wake up.
Just heard about Lenalee...
She's getting married.
How could you, Lenalee!!!
How could you even
consider getting married
without telling
your older brother?
Am I even gonna be a part
of the wedding party?
Sorry about this, but
sometimes it's the only way
we can wake him up,
he sleeps pretty hard.
So...
We're running short on time,
so as soon you two are briefed,
you'll need to leave ASAP.
What?!
You expect me to work with him?
Why?
Uh, yes.
You're on this
assignment together.
What's going on with you two?
Are you guys already
off to a bad start...?
How come?
They didn't exactly meet
on good terms now did they?
Ah...
My decision stands!
A fragment of Innocence was
discovered in southern Italy...
But we've got word
that an Akuma
is already en route
to grab it...
You two will head
there immediately.
Destroy the enemy and secure
the Innocence at all costs...
You'll have to time to look over
the dossier on the way there.
Good luck to you.
Do I really have
to wear this thing?
It's standard dress for
a professional exorcist...
It was created for battle,
so the material is
exceptionally robust.
Hey, where've
you been hiding...?
I've been looking all
over the place for you.
Timcanpy showed me your past.
He's equipped with
a recording device
so we can monitor your progress.
Be safe!
We'll see you soon!
Hold on!
Give me a sec!
We don't have time for that now!
That's our train!
Wait, the train is moving?!!
I can't believe
we pulled that off.
Hey, we're just
getting started...
Uh... Tickets?
We're with the Black Order...
I believe we have
several reservations?
Yes, of course.
Follow me.
I'll show you to
your compartment.
Wait, we get... our own room?
Now this is the way to travel.
According to the dossier
we're heading to...
the ancient city of Mater.
I think I remember reading
about this place once.
It's been in ruins for decades.
Our target sounds interesting.
The Ghost of Mater...
I'm confused.
How in the world could
a ghost have anything
to do with Innocence?
Hey...!
Is that attitude necessary?!
Take a guess.
Y'know, you're a jerk.
Unexplained phenomena
are a common occurrence
where Innocence exists.
Really?
Innocence has
altered its own biology.
Of course it doesn't
happen overnight...
Most estimates
place the timeline
between Noah's Flood
and the present.
This may be due to the
crystal's mysterious power
trying to communicate with us
or any number of
unknown reasons...
but it seems that
Innocence always finds
its way into human hands.
The one thing we
still can't figure out
is why Innocence is causing
the strange phenomena.
So...
You're saying the existence
of a ghost in Mater
could be caused by Innocence.
Yes...
Because where mystery is
found, Innocence is nearby.
That's why the Order enlists
Finders like myself to conduct
thorough investigations
of these instances.
Mysteries like the
Ghost of Mater?
Yes... Precisely.
Hi... My name is Allen Walker.
It's certainly my
pleasure, Master Walker.
I am Toma, your
Finder for this mission.
Have you been doing this
since we got on the train?
It's a hobby of mine.
It looks interesting.
Master Walker, tell me,
are you at all familiar
with the Ghost of Mater?
I'm not.
It's fascinating...
The story harkens
back to the days
when the city fell into ruin...
The ghost was
originally an inhabitant
of the city before
it met its demise.
As people visited the city,
the ghost would draw
them towards his being,
in an attempt to
relieve his lonliness...
I hear stories about
disappearances all the time.
We Finders investigate
stories like this,
even if it's only
a vague rumor...
and most of the
time, they are...
But until we
determine its validity...
and whether or not Innocence
is directly involved...
we will stay for up to months at
a time investigating the claims.
As I said, most
of them do turn out
to be fake stories or
local legends gone awry...
but even when the rumors
turn out to be fact...
It's very rare for
Innocence to actually play
a major role in the plot...
However...
if there is even the
slightest hint of possibility
that Innocence is involved...
It immediately becomes
a top priority,
for the finders,
to inform the Order...
And then...
Exorcists show up
to finish the job.
Be ready to move in five.
That way!
Draw it in and grab it.
Get it closer.
Easy... Easy...
Go!
We've got 'em in the barrier!
Excellent...
that should buy us some time
until the exorcist's arrive.
Yeah, let's hope so.
But something tells me there's
another Akuma out there.
I think you may be right.
Please... No... No...!
There's another one!
The barrier! It's...
The Finder unit's
been wiped out...
every last one of them...
Wh-What should we do?
We need to find a way to get
the Akuma inside the barrier.
Quiet...
We simply don't have
the manpower to subdue
the Akuma now that
the other unit is gone.
It's only a matter of time
before it finds us here.
Guzol.
Lala, run!
No... I... I can't do that...
I'm going to stay by
your side until the end.
I have an idea, but I'm only
doing this as a last resort.
All of us must go
to whatever lengths
are necessary to ensure
the Ghost of Mater's safety.
Until the exorcists
arrive we must hold on.
Toma, how's it looking?
I can't get through.
Then let's hurry.
I hope everyone's safe...
Can you see the Akuma?
I can.
My left eye is equipped with
a sensor that can spot Akuma,
and more specifically, the
souls trapped inside of them.
...a cursed eye.
You should have told us that
from the start, short-stack...
Before we arrive, let's
get something straight...
I'm not nearly the
idealist you are.
Emotions have no place
on the battlefield.
If you get yourself hurt,
hinder the mission
and put the rest
of us in danger...
I'll leave you for dead.
In other words,
we're not partners,
so don't expect me to help.
Pleasant as always.
Right.
Still no response?
No.
That's strange.
The Finder unit should have
already risen the barriers.
They could survive a few
days in there, at least.
I see the barrier...
it's over there!
That must be the Ghost of Mater.
What?
Then where are the Finders?
It looks like they've
activated the barrier
in order to protect
the Ghost of Mater.
Instead of saving themselves...
they must be waiting
for the exorcists...
Oh no.
Then they did their job, Toma.
Agreed.
There's a light!
They're alive!
Master Walker!
Leave him alone...
You and I should hurry.
The barrier won't last long.
Please Exorcist.
Stupid...
That's what happens when
you attack with no plan.
Now it's time for battle.
Mugen...
Unsheathe.
Innocence...
Activate!
Mugen.
Summon Misfortune!
Underworld...
Creatures...
First Illusion!
Finder, tell me the
release code for the barrier.
There's not much time.
Have you come to
save us... Exorcist?
Just give me the code,
you don't want your death
to be for nothing now do you?
Fine...
The code is...
Have Hope.
You must protect...
the Innocence...
Have you come to
save us, exorcist?
You're safe.
Ghost of Mater.
Just be careful, Timcanpy.
He's too strong.
It's changing!
What's happening?
The soul trapped inside
it is being distorted!
I am... an Akuma!
It spoke!
My new form is born from
the darkest of matter...
Thank you for all
your help, Exorcist!
It appears I'm all grown up!
How is that possible...?
The Akuma evolved?!
Aren't you clever?!
Kanda!
I'm not here to help you.
Acting on your emotions is
what got you into this mess...
You'll have to take
care of it yourself.
Fine then...
As long as you have
the Innocence
there's no need
for me to worry.
I'll catch up with
you two later,
after I destroy this Akuma.
You will die...
Not me!
Toma, keep an eye on him.
On Master Walker?
No, on that Akuma.
Yes, sir.
There's no way the kid
can defeat that thing...
He's in way over his head.
I see the ghost has
made his escape...
Well, that's fine...
I'll make plenty of time
to deal with him later...
But first...
I get to take your life.
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
Wait...
That's not an Akuma...
It's a fake!
I'm right... behind you.
What the...
There's two of me.
The Akuma has evolved
into an extremely dangerous
form using the souls
of the Finder's its murdered...
To make matters worse,
it gained the ability
to copy others, putting us
in a difficult situation.
Next time on D. Gray-man:
"Old Man of the Soil and
a Lonely Night's Aria."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.