Madame Lulu Bell...
Madame Lulu Bell!
Wouldn't you like
to get out of bed...?
Oh won't you please wake up!
Actually... I'm awake.
Oh good, then hurry
and let's go!
All those Exorcists are still
alive and waiting for us!
And thanks to your
awesome strategy
those goody-goodies got
split up into two groups...!
I can't wait to take
one of them out for good
and tell the Earl
what we've done!
I need to learn more about them.
You're overthinking it...
We should just get out
there and try something!
If we try and fail,
my Master won't have
any praise for me, will he?
But where are you going then?!
Madame Lulu Bell?!
I need a shower.
Madame Lulu Bell...
what are we doing?
This bridge is really scary!
What'd you stop
like that for, huh?!
I'll save it... for last.
Huh...? What does that mean?!
Please wait for me, Mistress!
I found it.
It doesn't work.
That's what I thought.
We could be too
far away from them
or maybe it's because we can't
get a signal in this valley...
Anyway, I don't think
we're going to be able
to communicate
through our Golems here.
What do you think we should do?
Keep moving...
We need to find a way to contact
Lavi and Lenalee as
soon as possible...
I'll bet if we could
get out of this Valley
we'd be able to
pick up a signal.
Then let's go.
I'm still really hungry...
Help us, somebody please help!
Just stay calm...
We have to pass
through this valley
if we want to get
to the other side!
Fine, then let's hurry...
Don't push me!
Maybe... we should try
to take it slow and easy.
Yeah, I think
that's a great idea!
Could that be...
A village...
It sure is.
This seems like a strange
location for a village.
But I'll bet someone here knows
how to get across the valley.
You're right, and with any luck,
we may be able to
score a meal, too...
Just tell us... What'd you
do with the statue, Selim?!
We won't leave you
alone until we know,
so unless you want to get
hurt, start talking, thief!
I didn't do it...!
You have to give me
a chance to explain!
Explain what...?!
Everything you say is a lie!
No, I'm not lying!
Stop it...!
Won't you at least
listen to him?
Don't waste your
breath, Katia...!
I'm sure that no one here
would believe me anyway...
Go ahead...
Try your best...
Come and kill me...
Do it!
You heard him.
Okay, if that's what
you really want!
Who's there?!
I haven't seen them before.
Hey... This doesn't
concern you...
Oh, I assure you,
gentlemen, we mean no harm.
My friend and I are
a little bit lost
and we're hoping you
could give us directions...
Yes, and maybe you could
even help us find a meal?
Krory, wait!
They're Akuma...
just show yourselves...
What the...
Do you see any
more of them around?
Not yet... I think that's all.
Oh good...
No...! Please don't run away!
We're never gonna eat.
What was that?!
Who are you guys...
and what are you doing here?
It's okay, there's no
reason to be afraid...
I don't mean to interrupt
but they're coming back.
We must kill the monsters, men!
You're right, we'll
never taste food again!
Let's get outta here!
They got away!
Just let 'em go...
No point in chasing 'em.
Selim...
It went just like we planned...
Yes...! Did ya hear that...
Everything's
working perfectly...
Isn't that great...
Be careful...
One who's quick to
speak of success
is usually quick to fail.
Our plan has just begun, Mimi.
Yes, I understand!
A stone statue moved by itself?!
Are you sure?
Positive...
It's the truth...
But since I'm a
wanderer no one trusts me,
they always assume
I'm lying to them...
although I suppose
they have good reason.
Selim, please, tell
us exactly what you saw.
It was last night...
I got back to
the village late...
I'd taken my time coming back
from hunting in the mountains.
Hey, what's the matter, Tannon?
No... but that's impossible...
Statues can't move like that!
Even though I saw her
do it with my own eyes...
I still can't believe
that something
made of stone could
walk out here like that.
But that's what happened...!
I did not take the statue!
Well, it's certainly
an intriguing story.
You shouldn't be surprised
that ordinary people
don't believe such
things are possible.
So you mean...
Do you guys believe me?
Right now, we're most
interested in whatever
is causing the
statue to move around.
There were Akuma back there...
Do you know of--
What are you doing out here?!
That's the girl
from the village!
Let her go... I know her...
Selim!
Pardon me!
There's plenty of meat here,
if you'd like some more.
It's delicious!
Yeah, thank you very much!
Katia's father happens to
be the mayor of our village
and she's always
getting in the way.
For a long time now,
all of the villagers
have believed
that the stone statue's
like our guardian angel...
and that as long as
it was in our possession
the land would
always be peaceful.
So you can understand
why my father
and the other men became worried
when they learned
it had disappeared.
Selim said he'd seen it walking
into the mountains and in
their fear they blamed him...
And what about you, do you
believe I'm a liar, too, Katia?
No, I've always believed in you!
Listen to me... you're
not a bad person, Selim!
Quit lecturing me...
You act like
my sister or something.
Selim showed up at our
village only a short time ago
and my father and
the other villagers
don't trust him very much.
Oh, I see... That doesn't
help things, does it?
By the way, I was wondering
what brought you to our village?
We only came to
ask for directions.
We're trying to
cross through the valley
and end up on the
other side of the mountains.
Why didn't you say so,
past the village,
you'll see a
suspension bridge...
If you cross it you'll
be on the other side
of the mountain in no time.
Oh, thank you...!
That's incredibly
helpful... isn't it?
Yes, it is...
But it looks like,
we shouldn't leave this
village behind just yet.
Yes... do you suspect
it's Innocence as well?
A legendary stone
statue suddenly
begins moving around by itself
and Akuma are starting to
appear at a nearby village...
Yeah, I'd say it's very possible
we're dealing with Innocence.
What's Innocence?
It's something that's
extremely valuable to us
and it causes mysterious
phenomena whenever it's around.
Besides, now that
Akuma are in the area
we can't abandon
the villagers...
We have to stick around
and get to the bottom
of what's happening
with this statue.
Thank you so much...!
If we find the statue then we
can prove Selim's innocence!
Just leave it to us...
We owe you for the
meal, anyway, don't we?
That's true!
It's this way...
I'm sure I saw the
statue take this path...
Just follow me.
Listen, Selim, this is probably
going to be dangerous.
Yes, it's very likely we'll be
running into more Akuma
and it'd be much safer
if you waited here.
But I can't...!
The paths up here are winding
and hard to navigate...
Without me guiding
you, you'll get lost
and we won't be able
to find the statue.
We can't let you--
No...!
Don't you see?
If I bring the statue
back to the villagers
then maybe they'll
begin to trust me...!
Right, Katia?!
It's risky...
I know that, but I have
to come with you, please!
Alright, lead the way...
But if we get into
any fighting up there,
I want you to promise
me you'll stay down...
You got it... Thank you, Allen!
Now stay close, okay?
Selim!
What is it?
Just be careful okay...
Yeah...
And let the games begin.
Oh, good... You're awake.
Yeah... Where are we?
In a carriage.
In a larger sense, we're
on our way to meet Bookman.
The plan is to get you
healed as soon as possible...
Then we can get
back to our mission.
I'm sorry, Lavi.
Hey... did you ever get in
touch with Allen and Krory?
Uh-uh, I wasn't
able to get through...
There's no signal and
I think all of the mountains
around here are preventing us
from connecting
through the Golem.
Oh, I hope they're okay.
Well now, as long
as they stay together
I'm sure they'll be fine...
As a matter of fact...
I can almost hear 'em
whining right now...
Twenty bucks says
they're starving.
Probably right...
For now, we need
to just concentrate
on getting you well again,
young lady, so we can join 'em.
Allen, Krory...
Where are you?
These rocks are incredible!
I know...
over the years, rainwater
and the elements
have eroded them and
created this terrain...
It's easy to get lost out
here so we have to be careful.
What's wrong?
I see it over there!
So that's it...
That's what you saw, Selim?
That's her, there's
no mistaking it.
Then let's follow her, quickly!
What's that?
They're the ancient ruins...
This may be the biggest...
It was an old temple
or something.
They fell for it...! Let's go...
Things are going just as
Madame Lulu Bell planned!
If a legendary stone statue
were to start to move...
What do you suppose
people would think?
Well, I guess they'd have a hard
time believing it at first...
They'd probably think their eyes
were playing tricks on them.
Yes... but then...
...there are other people
who see things differently.
Who would that be?
Exorcists, of course.
I see now!
Madame Lulu Bell?
The Excorcists are always
seeking Innocence...
This trap will prove
irresistible to them.
And then...
Leave the rest to me.
Just a little longer...
Wait for Madame
Lulu Bell to give the signal!
This place is full of statues!
Where do you suppose the one
we're looking for is hiding?
There it is!
They've come.
Be careful!
Don't worry...
Everything seems fine!
Ready...
And go!
Whoa, what's going on?!
I dunno, just be ready!
Allen, are you alright?!
Missed my chance!
Oh no, it didn't work...!
Everyone kill them!
Selim, take cover!
My my... This will
be quite a feast!
There's so many of them!
Nice work, thanks!
Are you alright?
Yeah, thanks to you!
Wait, where are you going...?
Do you have another plan?
I quit.
What?!
There's no point in
fighting any more
so I'm going back.
Hey, wait a second!.
You can't just change
your mind like that...!
You're acting like a cat you
know, but then, you are a cat.
Retreat! Fall back now!
Our enemies are getting away!
Damn...
Hey... where are you guys?!
Come over this way...
I think I found her!
Back here.
The real one?
It sure is... This is her...
She's the village's
guardian angel.
Everyone will be so
happy she's been found
and peace will return
to the people here.
Allen... why do you
think the Akuma retreated
in the middle of a battle?
I don't know...
Maybe they thought
they couldn't defeat us,
but by using that statue
they had us trapped,
so it doesn't
make much sense.
I don't understand it, either.
Hey, look, there it is!.
It's just like Selim told us!
This bridge gives us a
way to cross the valley,
and once we're over
the mountain range
we should be able to
contact Lavi and Lenalee...!
C'mon!
They destroyed it...
Damn them...!
They're obviously hoping
to keep us stranded here
by any way possible!
What is it, is something wrong?
Oh... Just thought
I saw something...
Well, at least we were able
to delay our enemies for now.
Taking out the bridge
bought us some time
before they got
together with the others...
Good strategy, Madame Lulu Bell!
Yes, I know, failure isn't
any fun at all, is it...?
We'll have to make sure
we succeed next time, then.
Lavi continues on his journey,
faithfully protecting
our injured comrade...
while silently, the evil hand of
an assassin closes in on him...
Next time on D.Gray-man:
"Iron Fan Maid."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!