No! Mei Ling!
We lost her.
Why did it take Mei Ling...?
What could it possibly want?
It would appear that the Akuma
are after the
girl's crystal ball.
Do you know something...
Did her grandfather
tell you why?
Yeah... They want the ball?
Yes...
I believe it's very likely
that Mei Ling's crystal ball
is indeed, Innocence...
I'll provide more details later.
Hurry and go now...
The girl is in grave danger...
Please save her...
Mei Ling is everything to me.
Yes, sir!
Extend!
What?
Now, let's go!
Yes, lets!
It looks like there's
a lot of Akuma
at the lake up ahead of us!
We've gotta hurry!
Where am I?!
Look around... Isn't it obvious?
The lake... What's happening...?
Don't you remember...?
You threw the
ball into the lake
and now it's caused a whirlpool.
Well done!
You may have uncovered
something very valuable to us
called Innocence!
Innocence...
But if it's your ball,
does that mean it
contains Innocence?
You know what it is...
No, I don't!
It makes no difference
if you admit it or not...
I'll know the truth
when I drop you into it.
No one is able to
go near the whirlpool
but the ball belongs to you,
so let's see what happens...
Oh no... help me!
Mei Ling has had the
gift of telling fortunes
ever since she was
just a tiny little thing.
The ball was a family heirloom,
and when she touched
it she talked like she had
seen the future
in it; clear as day.
And everything she
foretold always came true...
It was amazing, really,
how accurate and
vivid the visions were.
When her predictions
came to pass
the townspeople were happy,
and I think that's what
really made her want to
keep telling fortunes...
Mei Ling has always found her
happiness in pleasing others.
But then, one night
about a month ago,
my heart jumped in my chest
when I heard her scream.
She became afraid
of the crystal ball,
and refused to even go near it.
I asked her what she saw,
but she just looked
at me and trembled...
and she seemed so petrified
of the ball and so fragile...
I'm telling you, she was almost
on the verge of a breakdown.
And that's why I took
the ball out to the lake
and threw it overboard...
I was scared and
I wanted to protect her.
An ordinary crystal
ball couldn't cause
a lake to dry up
like that, could it?
It's got to be something else.
But we suspect we're not dealing
with an ordinary crystal ball.
What?
If we're right and this ball
does turn out to be Innocence,
then your granddaughter...
Hey, you okay?!
You shouldn't get distracted!
Say what...
Crap!
That wasn't much fun.
Hey, are you okay, Krory
I'm fine...
Look... there...
Ah hell, it's another one!
And it seems to be
carrying someone!
What?!
No... No!
A little girl...?!
What could they
possibly be doing?
Well lookie here...
Found you...
You're actually very
lucky, you know that!
Oh, we know...
But you guys, not so much
'cause we're gonna nail ya...
That we will!
Really...?!
What're you gonna do?!
Whaddya think?
We're gonna fight!
And kick ass!
Hold on!
Mei Ling... Wait!
Lenalee!
Oh no!
Too late!
It dropped her!
What was that?
I don't want to!
No!
What's happening to it?!
Can you see anything?
There she is...!
Innocence, activate!
Wait, Lenalee!
Open your eyes...!
Are you okay, Mei Ling?!
What is it doing?
It's sucking up all the water.
Is that it?
Yes...
That's my crystal ball...
The one grandfather
and I threw into the lake.
Mei Ling...
you need to know that that's
no ordinary crystal ball.
It's an Innocence fragment
and I'm pretty sure
you've been chosen
to be the Accommodator
of that Innocence.
What does that mean?!
Innocence...
It's the source of miraculous
powers that have the ability
to cause all sorts of
mysterious phenomena...
It also gives humans the power
to fight the Millennium Earl
and all of the demons
under his control, who hope
to destroy this world...
Innocence is humanity's only
hope against these evil forces.
And so... for us,
Innocence is life
but for demons, or Akuma,
it's something to
be hated and hunted.
Each piece of Innocence
can only be controlled
and used to its full
purpose by one person,
known as an Accommodator...
Accommodators of
Innocence are the only people
who can gain the
power to fight Akuma
and they're also known as...
The Exorcists.
Exorcists...
So that's really Innocence...
It is?
Yes and you're probably
the Accommodator
of that Innocence, Mei Ling...
Which would mean that,
well, you're one of us.
I'm like you... an Exorcist...
Wow, looks like it's expanding.
Now!
Idiot Akuma!
What's it doing?!
Alright then how about this!
No...
No!!!
Nooooo!!
Come on... Let's go!
Mei Ling...
Allen...! Lenalee, hey!
Are you both alright?
Yeah, what's going on?
Well...
No... no... Never!
It's okay.
Please don't make me...
I can't...
I can't touch it again!
About a month ago,
the crystal ball showed me
a different kind of future.
It was dark, and terrible,
and full of death.
I didn't mean to.
I promise I was
only trying to help...!
I love the people here
and I wanted to do
what I could to make them happy!
Why did this happen...? Why??!
It's alright...
Don't worry about it.
Poor little thing...
I wonder what vision
the ball revealed to her?
I'll bet... that Mei Ling
saw her own future.
But then why would that
frighten her so much?
Because that girl's an
Accommodator of Innocence,
so the future that she
got to see in the crystal ball
must've been one
of her as an Exorcist.
We all know that we've
chosen a dark and bloody path,
but we still have hope because
we can't see how the story ends.
That's right... and she can.
Listen to me...
I have to stay here, but
I want you to go on home.
Really?
Yes, really.
I want you to go take
care of your grandfather
and enjoy every
minute of your life
and forget all about this...
Don't worry about
Innocence or the future.
Mei Ling...
I'm so glad I got to meet you.
Wait!
Yes?
Lenalee... don't go.
What was that?!
What's happening to it...?
Is it moving now?
It looks like the
Innocence is beginning
to spin out of control.
Out of control?
Yes...
Your Innocence has real power,
the power to show
you future events...
I'm guessing it might
even be the force
that literally connects
the future and the present
for just an instant in time...
So, then...
The Innocence might lose control
if it was separated from its
Accommodator and the present
and was somehow directly
connected to the future.
However it happened,
we have to hurry
and stop it before
things get worse.
I'll help...
Mei Ling... there's
something I want to say, okay?
Sure.
You should know that the
path you're about to take
may lead you to an even
more painful, harder future
than the one
you've already seen...
Knowing that,
do you still want to do it?
Yes!
Okay then...
I'll be beside you all the way.
Yeah, alright!
Come on. Let's do it!
I'm feeling hungry!
Yeah, it's time
to settle things.
How am I supposed to
do anything about this?
Extend!
Now, Lenalee!
We're counting on you!
Are you scared?
No!
Then you better hold on tight.
I will!
Innocence... activate!
Are you still alright?
Yes, I'm fine!
It's just for a
little bit longer, 'kay?
Okay!
Now Innocence...
Level Two release!
I'm so sorry for not
understanding you.
I didn't know you were
suffering, just like I was.
I think... we can finally
come together now.
Lenalee!
Did they make it?
They did it!
What's the matter?
Lenalee, will I really be
able to become an Exorcist?
Mei Ling...
Are you still scared...?
What you saw must've been awful.
It was... but...
it didn't show me everything
that's going to happen.
And maybe that could mean
there's more to the story
and there's a bright future
beyond what I could see then.
That's what I hope...
If I'm with you I'll be fine.
You're very brave...
you know that?
I've got you now!
Alright!
The water's back...
They must've gotten the
Innocence back under control.
That means Mei Ling has made
her choice then, doesn't it?
I do pray for her sake that
it was the right decision.
Ultimately, no one can tell if
the future will be good or bad.
I guess you're right...
and, either way
it's the future she's
chosen for herself.
Ah man...
Well, we somehow
managed to survive that.
It was a tough one this time.
Hey, look out there!
Unacceptable!
You are totally useless!
Begone.
What?!
Well, what do you think
we should do now,
Madame Lulu Bell?
I've been thinking about
this new turn of events.
I know, with a
new stupid Exorcist
on the scene and
her unknown powers
I don't know what
we're supposed to do next!
We'll report it... to Master.
To impress her beloved Madame...
Mimi mounts a strong,
solitary attack...
in the hopes of stealing Mei
Ling's new-found Innocence.
Next time on D. Gray-man:
"Madame Lulu Bell's Bell."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!