Kanda's missing?!
Innocence was
discovered in ruins
just outside the city and
he was sent to collect it.
But it's been a week now
since we've had any
contact with either Kanda
or the Finder that he
took along with him.
The man who took her identified
himself as "Vittorio."
Vittorio?!
The swordfighter that's been
living for a thousand years?!
The Innocence is healing him!
Oh, no!
Kanda!
Allen, wait!
You shall die with honor...
Kanda!
There's a pulse...
He's still alive!
Of course I am.
You know I don't die easily.
I can see that...
Kanda!
Allen seems to be holding up
against Vittorio's attacks,
but I don't know for
how much longer...
The Innocence is contained
in Vittorio's sword...
It's very deadly...
Unfortunately
Anti-Akuma Weapons
can only take so much damage.
How did he get that sword
in the first place...?
Can we somehow get his
weapon away from him...?
No, that will do
nothing to stop him...
Why?
He is...
He's been enslaved by the
Innocence, both body and soul.
Enslaved?
Yes.
And we have no
idea where Vittorio
could have gained access
to a sword like that...
I don't believe he'd physically
be capable of handling the power
of the Innocence
using only his will,
like an Accommodator
would be able to,
so he actually needs that sword.
When confronted with
someone of great power,
the Innocence in his possession
begins to overcome his will,
forcing him to go
beyond his natural limits
in order to defeat his enemy.
So the Innocence
is out of control?
Is that why you suppressed your
Innocence while fighting him,
Kanda, so you wouldn't
activate Vittorio's?
He can't do it...
Defeating Vittorio
is impossible.
Kanda!
You're bleeding Kanda.
This is no time to be a hero.
Stay here.
Watch him.
I will.
Innocence activate!
Lenalee!
I don't fight women...
Now begone.
You will die with honor...
Stop it!
Claudia, its you... wait...
Did this man take you hostage?
No one can make me go back...
You can try all you want but
I'm staying right where I am.
Please give a message
to my father and Paletti.
Tell them I will never return.
Wait a minute this isn't...
Claudia, come back!
I cannot promise this
will cure him, but...
...you may apply it
to his wounds anyway.
Thank you, we will...
And later, would you
tell them the story?
Yes, of course.
How's Allen?
I think he's going to be fine...
He nearly went into shock
when he couldn't move
his arm any longer,
but it didn't last long
and he's improving now.
I think the nerves in
his arm were in paralysis,
but it was only temporary.
That's good to hear.
Uh Miss...
There's a story I think could
shed some light on
our situation.
I'd like you and
Allen to hear it.
Please.
After fighting Vittorio over
the course of several days,
Kanda was facing total
exhaustion and slept
in a nearby cottage nestled
at the base of the mountain.
While he was resting,
I used those few days
to survey the area
and speak to the locals
in hopes of finding
any additional information
that could help our situation.
Fortunately, it was in this
search I came across
this elderly woman,
who told me the story
of Sandra and Vittorio.
This story is an ancient
tale that took place
one thousand years ago.
The lord who had rule over
this entire land at the time
had a beautiful
daughter named Sandra.
When she had turned sixteen
great swarms of men
arrived from far away lands
to ask for the princess's
hand in marriage.
However, no matter
how empassioned
or noble the numerous
offers of marriage,
Sandra would not accept.
I will only be the wife of the
strongest man in the world.
Then, to test their strength,
the princess told the men
that they must fight Vittorio,
the sword fighter who had
protected her noble family.
Vittorio fought for her
even after the princess
took ill and passed,
and it is said that the
battle cries are still heard
one thousand years later...
The Sardini family's residence
is on the same plot of land
Princess Sandra use to live on.
I see...
So Vittorio's been
defending Claudia
because he thinks
that she's the Princess.
Of course...!
Every time he defeated an Akuma
going after the Innocence,
he would report back to Claudia.
The world's strongest man
has yet to appear, my lady.
He saw them...
...not as Akuma,
but as the men who were
proposing to Princess Sandra.
Let's see it was exactly
one month ago today
that Vittorio first appeared
in front of Claudia.
That's around
the same time Akuma
began infiltrating the area
surrounding the ruins...
But what was he doing
there up to that point?
He probably was using the ruins
as a safe haven to hibernate
and to patiently wait for any
opponents he had to battle.
What opponents?
As long as Vittorio
has the Sword of Innocence
in his possession...
Akuma will continue
to appear before him.
Wait, then what about Claudia?
I'm afraid she's
gotten herself involved
in a situation that
has no end in sight...
These destructive
battles will continue
unless we can figure out a
way to solve this problem
before its too late...
Are you crazy?
Your wounds haven't
even healed yet!
They're healed.
Look at that...
They're almost gone...
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to defeat Vittorio,
collect the Innocence
and then be on my way.
And how do you
plan to do that...?
Every time you cut him with
your Mugen he regenerates.
I'll figure something out.
I've got troubling news...!
Multiple Akuma were
just spotted ambushing
the ruins again and
are fighting with Vittorio!
Huh?
Stop it Kanda, you haven't
completely recovered...
Why don't you rest for another
day and then go back tomorrow.
You know I can't...
You want them to
steal the Innocence
while I'm here taking a nap?
We can hold them back.
Oh that's reassuring.
Just believe in us...
Lenalee and myself...
and Vittorio.
Vittorio?
He won't make it easy for
the Akuma to defeat him...
He can't afford to...
That's why the Innocence
will stay in his possession.
You've got a point...
If enough Akuma work together
and overwhelm him, then
Claudia will be in danger...
Lenalee and I could be there
in a matter of seconds
to protect her safely.
So please, just
stay here and rest.
Try thinking of a strategy
for collecting the Innocence
inside Vittorio's sword.
Try thinking...?
Are you giving me orders now?
Sorry, Kanda...
But right now your brain is your
best asset, so just use that.
Get back here!
Pedro! Keep an eye
on him, will ya?
Of course.
I can't believe it, he really
is giving it some thought.
Vittorio!
Vittorio...!
Please listen to what
I'm about to say...
You don't have to
fight any longer.
The fact is Princess Sandra
died a very long time ago...
You were never told
and now a thousand years
of pointless fighting
has gone by...
Do you hear me?
The princess is alive
and it is her wish
that I continue to
fight in her honor...
It is my duty to
cater to her wishes
no matter how
extreme the request.
Come.
Please, wake up to reality...
There's no one
for you to protect.
Your fight is over!
It's never over!
You loved Princess Sandra.
That's why you don't
want to let her go.
No one is faulting you for that!
I serve the princess.
I follow the orders that
are given to me, nothing more!
This is a big misunderstanding.
He thinks you're
Princess Sandra...
Please, you've got to help us.
You're the only one
who's able to stop him.
Either do something now
or this will never end...
You'll be stuck
with him forever,
now is that what you want?
Maybe it is.
Vittorio saved me from
a life I didn't want,
where I could no longer make
a single decision on my own...
I felt like a captive.
At first I was scared.
He frightened me and I didn't
understand his purpose...
I expected the worst
but all he would do
is report to me and
quietly leave the house.
And then everything
was different...
One night he appeared before me
in my room and
asked me a question.
Why are you crying, my lady?
My father's forcing me
to marry someone I do not love!
Vittorio helped me escape
from that horrible situation.
Lay down your sword!
Why can't you realize
that all of your fighting
just puts Claudia's
life in danger!
What keeps Vittorio
alive also attracts Akuma...
You'll never have a chance
at a normal life being
anywhere near him!
This is what I mean when I say
you're too soft, Short Stack!
Kanda...?
You're coming with me!
I welcome your challenge.
Die!
No!
He refused to give up his sword,
so I had to improvise.
Vittorio!
I'm afraid... of losing...
No...
It's something else.
I want to lose.
The day I lose is the day
the pain will finally end.
But I... I can't handle it
if she becomes wife
with another man...
I can't lose...
I want to keep winning...
for the rest of eternity.
Vittorio...! Vittorio!!
I'm here now...
Don't leave me!
I don't want you
to fight anymore...
Let's go someplace
quiet, just you and I.
Princess...
I have... a confession.
I know you are
not Princess Sandra.
I knew she passed
away centuries ago...
However...
Fighting for you
was one of the greatest
honors of my life.
All that I ask... is that
you live for yourself
just like Sandra did...
so many years ago.
Oh, Vittorio.
Vittorio!
No!!!
Don't leave me!
Please... Wake up, please!
Three days later...
Claudia returned to the
Sardini Family's residence...
and packed up her belongings
before leaving again.
She chose to decide the course
of her own life in the end...
just as he had wished.
So, apparently Lenalee
is dating Russell
from the Science Division.
Can you believe it?
As they head into town
looking happy and carefree,
they're followed
by you know who...
Mister Paranoid McJealousy!
Find out what happens
on the next episode of
D. Gray-man: "Lenalee's Love."
Bring forth salvation
to poor Komui's soul!