[gasps]
Huh. What do we have here?
Where are my manners?
I haven't greeted ya yet.
Good evening, my friends.
Well, now. You haven't
changed a bit.
Have you, you fat bastard?
How long have you been in here?
I don't recall seeing you.
Or perhaps you've been hiding
right under our noses this
entire time, is that it?
I'm aware that
your lady companion
has the ability to
conceal your presence.
That was very clever
of you, albeit cowardly.
[chuckles]
[ROAD]
Hm?
[ROAD] So, Tycki. Did you
change your cigarette brand?
[MILLENNIUM EARL] You're also
using it to run from your debts,
aren't you?
[chuckles]
Look, I didn't come here
to listen to your
blathering, old man.
So fight me or get lost.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
"Get lost"? Ha-ha!
Last time I checked, Noah's
Ark was my own property.
[chuckles]
Till you jumped ship.
It might as well be a
duck that lost its wings
to fly out of Edo.
Since it was cursed...
...by the traitor to the Noahs,
the one they call
"The Fourteenth."
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
So I was right about you.
You really are the person
the Fourteenth selected to
be known as "The Player."
"The Player"?
What's he mean?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
In any case,
I'm sorry to say you've
arrived too late.
The heart of this Ark has
already been transferred
into the new one.
Without the heart,
it's impossible to
operate this vessel.
Player or not, you're
helpless to change fate.
You've made a grave
error, Cross.
And now, you'll never be able
to leave this place again.
[laughs]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
When this is all over...
[MILLENNIUM EARL] ...Noah's
Ark will become a coffin
that sucks the life out of
these pitiful Exorcists.
[laughing]
No, don't!
You're still bleeding!
It's over!
Allen, no!
Isn't that my sword?
Ooh. Just look
at that animosity!
[laughs]
[yells]
Be careful!
[singing]
[ALLEN]
Something's controlling me!
It's Carte Garde.
Maria stopped me!
[CROSS]
Cut it out!
You can't afford to lose your
head, you foolish apprentice!
Tell Maria to let go
of me, right now!
Don't fight the Earl
just out of hate.
Don't go, Lero!
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Thank you for your service.
So sorry you had to play along
with these errant children.
[LERO]
It was a nightmare, Lero!
[laughs]
But as a result, my dear
Tyki has finally awakened.
The boy had a nasty habit
of subconsciously suppressing
the Noah inside him.
He carries the
"pleasure" memory.
I have a soft spot for that.
[LERO] Let's settle into
our new home, Lero!
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Indeed!
Farewell then, Exorcists!
[CROSS] This place won't
last much longer.
[CROSS] You two. I assume
you know my mission?
Destroying the Akuma
plant, right?
[CROSS]
We're not far from it now.
Are you saying it's
inside Noah's Ark?
[CROSS]
Get up, Allen.
I rescued you from that Noah...
...because there's something
that I need you to do for me.
North Crime should do it!
Only a few left now.
[music playing]
There's a new sound in the sky!
New sound?
But what?
Look there.
[MIRANDA]
What's that up in the sky?
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Just one
more step to completion.
So there's another Ark!
[MIRANDA]
Where's that one going?
It's taking to the sky.
But, Bookman,
that's the one that's carrying
Kanda and the others.
But if they're trapped in there,
what will become of them?
Take us to the plant,
would you, Tim?
[ALLEN]
Tim?
Where are we?
[CROSS]
Turn around.
[LENALEE, ALLEN gasp]
[CROSS] That's the egg for
magic bodies. The plant.
[LENALEE]
Really?
I wanted to dispose of
it as soon as possible,
but that's a tall order.
[LENALEE]
A barrier.
We don't have enough
time to dismantle it.
Besides, the egg's
being downloaded
to the new Ark as we speak.
Then, as soon as it's
finished transferring,
the old Ark will disappear,
and we'll go with it.
[ALLEN, LENALEE gasp]
Which is why I'm asking
you to help me, Allen.
[ALLEN]
Me?
That's right. You will
operate the Ark.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[CROSS]
That should cancel the download
and prevent the Ark
from vanishing.
What? I don't understand!
[CROSS] Stop whining
and do as I tell you!
Hey, wait a sec!
I wanna fix this, but I
don't know the first thing
about steering this ship!
[CROSS]
This isn't optional.
Master.
Damn. It's already underway.
[CROSS]
On!
Abata! Ura! Masarakato!
Hope this works!
Baru!
That spell ought to
delay the downloading.
In the meantime,
prepare to steer.
But you still haven't
told me how to do that.
The heart of the Ark.
Uh, what heart?
[CROSS] I'll open a special
room. Follow Tim's lead.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
You'll know what to do.
[ALLEN]
Huh?!
Oh, no, Allen!
You're our only hope,
kid. Don't screw up.
[LENALEE screams]
[ALLEN]
Only hope? The heart?
Wait, didn't the Earl say
something about a heart before?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
You've arrived too late.
The heart of this
Ark has already
been transferred
into the new one.
[gasps]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
The download is almost complete.
Soon, the Ark and those
foolish Exorcists will perish!
[laughing]
Where am I?
Master? Lenalee?
[CROSS]
The heart of the Ark.
I'm not sure if I'm
in the Ark now.
[VOICE] Not even the
Earl knows this room.
This is the Fourteenth's
secret place.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
You're--
That's my key. See it?
Your key?
Timcanpy?
[SHADOW]
Yes, my Timcanpy.
Timcanpy belongs to my
Master. He isn't yours.
[SHADOW]
Timcanpy. Allen.
Together, you are the Player.
"Player"?
[gasps]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
So I was right about you.
You really are the person
the Fourteenth selected
to be known as "The Player."
That's right.
I heard the Earl
talking about that too.
[ALLEN]
What's the Player? Who are you?
You're the Fourteenth,
aren't you?
Why'd you choose me?
[gasps]
[ALLEN] Where's this uneasy
feeling coming from?
[CROSS]
You stupid kid!
[ALLEN] M-Master,
you're hurting my ears.
[CROSS] Quit dawdling
and stop that download!
[LENALEE]
The General has a radio too?
You're in, aren't you?
Can you hear my voice?
Answer me!
Lenalee! Yeah,
I hear you just fine.
I'm confused though.
What is this place?
[CROSS] No time!
Is there a piano in there?
[ALLEN]
What?
[CROSS]
A piano! Do you see one?
Yeah, it's right here.
[CROSS] Good. Then I
need you to play it.
That's the heart. It's
what controls the Ark!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
That's the heart?
[CROSS] The Earl doesn't know
about the room you're in,
which means he has no idea
there's another
heart to the ship.
We've got the advantage.
Get the song from Tim.
Master, I know you're
depending on me here,
but I've never played
a piano in my entire life.
I can't even read sheet music.
There's no way I
can steer the Ark!
[CROSS]
You can and you will, boy!
You're the one with the title.
[ALLEN]
Title? But I don't even--
[LENALEE]
Allen?
[ALLEN]
Yeah?
I can't say I
understand all of this,
but if the General believes
you can make it happen,
then I know that it's possible!
You have the power to
turn this around, Allen!
We came all the way to Edo
so we could help the General
carry out his mission.
If we give up now, everyone
who helped us get this far
will have been lost for nothing!
[CROSS]
You can play that song.
In fact, you're the
only one who can!
Understand? If you
play it right now--
[ALLEN]
Master!
[CROSS] ...not only will
you stop the download,
you'll control the Ark at will!
No, wait! Master!
It's up to me.
This is crazy.
But I... I don't have a choice.
[SHADOW]
You can play it.
[gasps]
After all, it's your melody.
Is that... the score?
[ALLEN]
It is.
And now for the finale!
The noises... they're fading.
Please, Time Record,
I'm begging you!
Stop time for Noah's Ark, now!
Isn't my power enough?
What more do I need to do?
Just save my comrades. Please!
Kanda's gone.
So we didn't only lose
Daisha, but him as well.
Lavi.
If only I had tried harder...
[MILLENNIUM EARL laughing]
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Yes, cry,
cry! It's all gone forever.
[chuckles]
[ROAD] You sound happy,
Lord Millennium.
[LERO]
Lero.
[MILLENNIUM EARL laughs]
[LULU BELL]
Well, are you pleased, Master?
[ROAD]
Seems like it.
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Why would
you ask something like that?
[LULU BELL]
Because you say you're happy,
but if you ask me,
you look miserable.
The fact of the matter is,
you're concerned about the
Fourteenth, are you not?
[LERO]
Are you, Lero?
[MILLENNIUM EARL] That's
ridiculous, of course not!
My nose is running, that's all.
I wonder if I'm catching a cold.
I'm pretty sure that came
from your eyes, Lero.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Don't be preposterous.
You're seeing things.
Now, let's be off, shall we?
Welcome to the
Fourteenth's secret room.
Even the Earl's never
seen this place.
He can't download what
he doesn't know exists.
Wait, I thought we fell.
What's happening here?
I thought this town
was destroyed.
But it's coming back!
[ALLEN] An unfamiliar song is
coming from inside my mind,
and its melody creates a
miracle before our very eyes.
On the next D.Gray-Man:
"Melody."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[CROSS]
Huh?
You idiot!
That's it, go play the piano.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
I don't know how to play piano!
[CROSS]
No excuses!
Why me?
[SHADOW sighs]
[LENALEE]
Huh?