It's the exact same
newspaper again...!
Same articles...
Same pictures...
Same horoscope.
It's five minutes to eight...
Three...
Two...
Please no!
I didn't... mean it... honey...
How could you cheat on
me again with that woman?
How many days in a row
is that now, you bastard?!
How many years have
we been together?
No...
It can't be...
That makes it
thirty times now...
Thirty times in a row that we've
lived October twenty-eighth.
Miranda, Miranda,
she's all bad luck...
Full of doom, full of gloom.
What a dumb and ugly duck...!
Looking for a job today,
who cares, you'll
just get chucked!
Miranda, Miranda,
she's all bad luck...
Full of doom, full of gloom.
What a dumb and ugly duck...!
Looking for a job today,
who cares, you'll
just get chucked!
Our town is stuck on
October the twenty-eighth...
The repetition is maddening...
Nothing changes...
Not a single thing.
Is Innocence there?
Maybe...
Could be...
No, probably.
Okay, you know how
I just said probably...?
It's more like maybe...
Or not at all because I really
don't know, to be honest...
Or maybe I do know.
Who can say for sure?
So, I'm not sure I... follow.
And what's to
follow, my friend...?
Apparently there's
a place out there
that's being endlessly rewound.
What does that mean?
Let me explain...
It appears as if time
and space have come
to a standstill in the town...
Causing a single day
to endlessly repeat...
Reever, come here!
I'm coming.
Here's everything
we have so far...
We first heard about
this from a wholesaler
who supplies a
liquor store in town.
On October twenty-eighth,
he received an order
to deliver ten barrels of red
wine for October twenty-ninth.
He attempted the delivery,
but was physically incapable
of entering the town,
as if a force field
were stopping him.
Since then, he's received
the exact same order
verbatim--everyday.
Wow... That sounds spooky.
Hold on, let me
get this straight...
It's still October
twenty-eighth even though
its almost December
now...? How strange.
We'd like to
investigate this matter.
But our Finders are having
trouble entering the city...
And because of that...
everything else we
know is just theory.
First off...
If this phenomenon
is being triggered
by some form of Innocence...
then Exorcists who
contain Innocence
may have the ability to enter
the town where others haven't.
But... If the Order's
investigation
illustrates that
this town really
is stuck in a time vacuum
on October twenty-eighth...
It's quite possible
that you won't be able
to leave once you get inside.
The town's basically cut off
from the rest of the world.
Well what do you think...?
Shall we go?
Uh... Yeah sure.
Careful, Lenalee...
So long.
I've never heard of
anything like this before.
So your new life...
you like it?
Do you mean the jobs...?
Or how I'm living
with the Order now.
I guess both.
I'm still getting
used to the work.
But I'm starting to feel
at home at the Order...
It really does feel like
a family... ya know?
Everybody's been
really nice to me.
Well...
Except for one
person in particular.
That's nice...
I'm glad...
and as for me...
It took me quite a
while to get used to it.
What...?
I thought you joined the Order
with your brother Chief Komui.
No at first I was
all by myself...
You have no idea how happy
I was when my brother joined me.
I didn't leave his side
for at least the first
few months he was here.
I find that hard to believe!
LENALEE!!!
Yeah I'm not sure
what to do with him.
Toma.
I've been expecting you.
Toma...
How are you?
Good, thanks.
So I take it you
haven't gotten inside yet.
Right.
That's as far as I can get...
Unfortunately the only
thing I know about
this town is the exterior wall.
It makes me wonder
if we'll be any different.
We won't know if we
don't give it a try.
Please be careful.
That was easier than I thought.
You're telling me.
I'm almost
disappointed in a way...
Now...
I wonder where the
Innocence could be hiding?
It's the exact same
newspaper again...!
Same articles...
Same pictures...
Same horoscope.
It's five minutes to eight...
Three...
Two...
Please no!
I didn't... mean it... honey...
How could you cheat on
me again with that woman?
How many days in a row
is that now, you bastard?!
How many years have
we been together?
No...
It's still happening...
That makes it
thirty-one times...
Thirty-one times in a row
that we've lived
October twenty-eighth.
How will I ever
escape this hell?
Why thank you...
Are you ready
for your cleaning...?
You're so sweet to comfort me.
What do you say we
split up and look for it?
We'll cover more
ground that way.
How about if we meet up at
that pub around lunchtime?
Sounds good.
Look...!
It's the bringer
of bad luck lady!
Yeah, there she is,
let's get her!
Nobody likes you,
nobody likes you...
Take this... witch!
No way...!
I can't believe she dodged it!
Heh...!
You know what kid,
it really isn't all
that hard to do
when you've had thirty
straight days of practice!
Huh?
Huh...?
I've never thrown that snake
at you in my whole life!
Peter...
You're gonna catch her bad luck
if you keep talking to her.
Miranda, Miranda,
she's all bad luck...
Full of doom, full of gloom.
What a dumb and ugly duck...!
Looking for a job today,
who cares, you'll
just get chucked!
Look out...!
She's beaming us with bad luck!
RUN RUN!!
Those brats...
I don't understand.
Why can't anyone else
see what's happening?
I...
I don't know if I can handle
another day without sun.
As I exit the alley
a carriage will splash
muddy water all over me,
then I will go home... again.
Oh my God! This has
never happened before!
But where did this
monster come from?
Is today the day I die...?
Could it really be tomorrow?
Will my suffering end?
Where is the Innocence?
You will tell me.
I'd let go of her if I were you.
There's someone else
I've never seen before...!
Oh God, please tell
me I'm not dreaming.
It's true...!
I'm actually living tomorrow!!
Come back!
Today is the happiest
day of my life!
Why, do you ask?
Because it's not today,
it's tomorrow!
I think I spoke too soon.
That's him...!
He's the one who
changed everything.
You and I really need to talk!!!
Welcome members of my family...
Let us all find success in
our quest for Innocence.
I've provided a
plethora of Akuma
to choose from
and use as you see fit.
So we'll be hunting Innocence.
That's right!
I'm ready to let loose...
I bet it'll be so much fun...
I have other work to
finish before I start,
but let me know
if you need my help.
Then...
maybe I'll go ahead and start up
the celebration with a bang.
What's it supposed to be?
Excuse me.
Don't ignore what I asked...
How did you lose her, Allen?
She ran off before
I could stop her...
But look...
At least we know
what she looks like now.
I guess so.
We can use the
drawing to find her.
Is it...
Is it that bad?
Uhh... yeah.
If I had known this
was going to happen,
I would never have split
us up in the first place.
The Akuma you fought...
Are you positive that it
said Innocence to her?
Yeah.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
You're gonna eat all that?!
I'm gonna get started...
'Kay...? 'Kay.
That was delectable.
Wow, you actually did it.
So about that woman again...
She's the key...
I think she'll be able to lead
us right to the Innocence...
We're sure lucky I found her.
Yeah right...
So how are your
investigation's going?
It looks like my brother's
theory is correct after all...
so... right after I
split with you...
I attempted to leave the town.
When I walked through
the edge of the village,
it just spit me right back in.
So... it's just as we feared.
Now we're stuck
in this endless loop
of a town along with everyone
else until we find a solution.
That's why we need to
get the Innocence ASAP.
Innocence?
That's her, Lenalee!
She's the one!
Wait! I'm sorry I screamed!
You're Exorcists?
We are, but why are
you running away?
We're here to help you.
I'm sorry...
I've been through a lot lately.
Yeah, hello...?
I'd like to place an order
for ten barrels of red wine,
I need it tomorrow.
This must be the place
Reever was talking about.
So... my name is
Miranda Lotto...
And I'm alone...
But I'm happy to find people
who can see what I see...
Yes, umm...
I would mention it to people
but they would just mock me...
This last month's been so hard
that I've contemplated suicide.
But I've learned
that the only way
to stay alive is to
dodge the snake.
I think she's...
Lost her mind.
Miss Lotto, tell me...
You've been able to
see the abnormalities
that are happening
here everyday?
I have...
but it's as if, everyone else in
town has no idea it's happening.
Please you have
to help me out...
I can't stand this
insanity anymore!
You saved my life from that
evil monster back there...!
You've saved me once you can
save me again, can't you?!
You need to calm
down, Miranda...
We'll help, but we need
to work together on this.
That sounds really good.
Something must have happened on
the first October twenty-eighth
to trigger the repetition...
any idea of what it could be?
How many times do
I have to tell you people?
It's always October
twenty-eighth here!
What's wrong?
Do you see those men
at the bar, Miranda...?
They're the only people
in town that have noticed
you're different than
everyone else aside from us.
I realize why you're the only
one this time warp affects...
and why you can see
things others cannot see.
It's because you're the one
who's in contact with the
Innocence that is causing
all these abnormalities...
Which is why these
creatures are here.
Innocence activate!
Lenalee.
Get Miranda to safety
while I handle this.
Your Dark Boots are quicker
than anything these
Akuma can muster.
I'll meet up with you later!
Be careful Allen!
I'll come back to help
you as soon as I can.
All three of these
Akumas are level Twos.
I finally find the
person that can save me
from this hell
and now he's gone!!
So this is the rewinding town.
Lero, wait, don't do this...!
Leroleroleroooo!
Who was that?
And Road Kamelot makes
a stunning appearance.
Pang Voice!
Feels like my
head's... splitting!
Hotter than flame its, ICE FIRE!
If you come in
contact with it...
Flesh rots instantly...
You wanna try it?
Let's slice him up...!
Let me go first!
Lets me do it...!
It'll be funnier
if I use my voice 'cause
his head'll explode!
I will slice you to pieces!
I'll make you rot!
Your brain will be mush!
One two three Scissors...!
One two three Rock...!
One two three Paper...!
One two...
You play dirty...!
How dare you interrupt a
game of Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Do you expect me to just
sit around and wait?
We must crush the Exorcist!
Crush him to death!
Stop.
You three are
having too much fun...
Need I remind you
that the mission is to
search for Innocence?
Return.
What just happened?
Where'd they go?
That's... a good... question...
There was a big booming
voice in the sky...
and then they were gone.
A voice?
So you wanted to
speak with us, Road?
That is correct...
Never go behind my back and
have all the fun without me!
The boy...
He's the one who carries
the eye of the cursed...
It makes me wonder what approach
I should take in his death.
Picking up on the scent
of the nearby Innocence,
the mysterious young
girl Road arrives
in the Rewinding Town
to stake her claim.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The Bad Luck
Woman's Innocence."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.