[BRANCH MEMBERS chattering]
[ALL]
One, two...
Okay, Allen.
Try making a fist
with your left hand.
Sure.
[SHIFU]
Okay.
All clear.
Looks like everything
checks out.
Ah! What a relief!
In addition,
his condition appears
to be better than ever.
[LO FWA]
Huh?
How do you know that?
[SHIFU]
Here.
I asked HQ to send us any
records they had on Walker.
I compared the data.
Take a look at his Innocence.
It's more completely
joined with his body.
While before it was unrefined.
Amazing.
Nothing's too surprising
at this point.
Remember the Chief said the will
of the Innocence kept him alive.
After all the obstacles
he's overcome,
how can you not think
he's loved by God?
[sighs]
You don't have time to
get lost in thought!
We still have several important
tests that need to be conducted.
Yeah, yeah.
[inhales, exhales]
[WONG]
Feeling tired?
Whenever I'm exhausted,
I drink tea.
Try it. It should help.
Thank you very much.
I heard they gave you
a clean bill of health.
Uh?
I'm impressed you healed
to this extent so quickly.
I guess there's no harm
saying when they first
brought you here, I wasn't
sure you'd recover.
[ALLEN]
It's all thanks to you
and everyone else's help
at the Asian Branch.
Don't downplay the suffering
you've had to endure
to reach this point.
You're being too modest.
Your innocence is restored
because you never gave up.
Thanks, Wong.
Chief Bak would like to see you.
Sure.
[gasps]
Are you all right?
Before that. There's
something I've gotta do.
Time to dig in!
Sorry, Wong. I can't
control my appetite.
Seems like a new arm
hasn't changed it.
Don't worry.
Can't have a meeting with
an empty stomach, right?
[BRANCH MEMBER A]
Here's more.
[BRANCH MEMBER B]
Have these, too.
We'll explain.
We saw your fight, Allen Walker.
Even though we're in the Black
Order and help the Exorcists,
we've never witnessed them
in combat first hand.
We've heard stories of course,
but never imagined
an actual fight with
an Akuma was so fierce.
[ALLEN]
Uh...
It dawned on us as
we watched you battle.
Compared to your job,
we have it pretty easy.
I'm ashamed to admit
it, but early on
we suggested to Chief Bak
that you be transferred.
Send you back to headquarters.
Please forgive us.
Uh. It's okay.
I've never seen
Innocence like yours.
It was incredible!
[gasps]
[door opens]
[BAK]
Uh?
I brought Walker in as
you asked, Chief Bak.
Come in. This way.
Oh man. Wow. This room
is pretty amazing.
[ALLEN gasps]
It's funny.
Huh?
My appearance...
It's similar to a clown.
Don't you think?
[BAK]
I didn't notice.
Oh. I heard the test
results came back
and showed there
weren't any problems.
Yep. Li Kei and the others
just gave me the full report.
Thank you, Bak.
For everything that
you've done for me.
How's the left arm?
Well, it's not exactly
back to normal yet,
but it'll do fine.
So I see.
What's wrong?
Hey, Chief Bak?
Uh?
What are you looking
so sad about?
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
[BAK]
A clown, huh? I can see it.
In that case, it would
be God's clown.
We'll call your Innocence
the Crown Clown.
Was it strong, Bak?
[BAK]
Hm?
You saw my Innocence.
Would you say it's strong?
Oh. Yeah! It's a powerful
Anti-Akuma weapon.
Rest assured.
That's good.
Then I'm finally ready to
join my comrades again.
Have you heard any news
if they're okay?
Yeah. They should
have reached Edo.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Understood.
Chief Bak! Headquarters called.
The line's restored.
Well then, Walker.
Looks like we'll talk later.
Okay.
[ALLEN]
One thing.
Even if Komui tells you
it's too dangerous,
I'm still going to ride the Ark.
You're not serious.
I'm looking over
the report you sent.
So his arm and body
are completely merged?
[BAK]
Yes.
It's proof Walker's mind and
Innocence have bonded.
Whereas before the
two were at odds.
[KOMUI]
Fascinating.
Furthermore, based on the
information in front of me,
his Innocence was unstable.
That left arm of his
was like a rough jewel.
Pure but unrefined.
Not quite an
anti-Akuma weapon yet.
It still needed some polishing.
It must have reacted
to Allen's emotions.
And whenever it
released that power,
it appeared similar to
Innocence being activated.
Looking back, it's obvious.
The records clearly show
that it's incomplete.
There's no comparison between
the old arm and the new one.
But who can blame him?
He's just a 15-year-old kid.
Governed by emotions.
Show me someone
his age who isn't.
This incident may have been
a blessing in disguise.
He could have gone his whole
life, living only for the Akuma.
Filled with suffering.
Sad and alone.
But that wasn't the case.
The battlefield drove
him into a corner.
And forced him to
acknowledge what he loved.
The need to save both
humankind and the Akuma.
His love is pure and
terrifying at the same time.
Yes. Isn't it?
Strong enough to change
him into a new person.
Reborn with the "Crown Clown"
to save both humans and Akuma.
However, there's one
thing I'm not sure of.
[BAK] Now that he's made
a comeback, is he content?
Will his choice bring him
the satisfaction he seeks?
One day we'll be strong enough
to cheat at cards again.
[ALLEN]
My mind is made up now.
I just need to push
forward on this path.
I'll keep walking
without stopping.
[LO FWA] So this is the
legendary Noah's Ark?
It doesn't look like a boat.
Are you serious, Jiji?
This thing is really a vessel?
I don't know and
that's not our job.
Stop talking and record data.
[ALL]
Right! Yes sir!
The Science Section
at headquarters
will determine
what it is or isn't
based on the
information we send.
Our task is simply to hand
over accurate data,
no matter the amount.
[SCIENCE SECTION chattering]
[NO. 65]
They're trying to bury us!
[REEVER] How's the analysis
comin', Johnny?
Um. Fine.
I've never seen this
much data, sir.
No time for complaining.
We've got Exorcists fighting
on the battlefield
who need these results ASAP.
[JOHNNY]
Y-Yes sir.
Well. Ha! For some reason
it reminds me of my office.
Hey Chief.
Try to walk between the pages.
[KOMUI]
That's no way to treat me.
Especially when I'm delivering
such good news.
Has there ever been a time
when your good news was
actually good, Chief?
It appears Allen
Walker's Innocence
has been fully restored.
What?
[SCIENCE MEMBERS]
Huh?
Hey! That's great news!
Our top priority is verifying
the Ark is a teleporting device.
And if so, can Allen
safely board it?
[SCIENCE MEMBERS]
Uh.
Understood!
We'll examine every last detail.
Those are your orders, got it?
[SCIENCE MEMBERS]
Yes, sir! We got it!
Headquarters, huh?
So cool!
The Science Section at the
Europe Branch is the best!
It's my goal to work
for them one day.
Me too.
[LO FWA]
Oh? Ah!
Welcome back, Allen!
You're home early!
Was there any trouble?
No trouble at all.
I just wanted to rush back
so I could have dinner
with you, Lo Fwa.
[LO FWA gasping]
Ah! Maybe I'll get
serious and apply!
Lo Fwa. This work would
get done a lot quicker
if there were three
people doing it.
We lost her.
[WONG]
We meet again.
This is the last time I'll
give you your medicine.
You know the drill.
Thank you, Wong.
Forgive me.
But perhaps you should
rest your arm a little.
You're right. Still,
I'm kinda anxious
to get the senses back
in my hand again.
[WONG]
I'm sure when your friends see
your Innocence revived it'll
send morale through the roof.
Yeah maybe, at least I hope so.
Lenalee was especially
shocked when I told her
you would no longer
be an Exorcist.
But I imagine she'll be even
more surprised to see you again,
stronger than ever!
What?
I guess with all the
excitement going on,
no one mentioned I was
the one who told Lenalee
and the others you were
at the Asian Branch.
You saw them?
Were they doing all right?
Yes.
I also escorted Miranda to the
docks to set sail with them.
What? Miranda's with them?
That's right. She did
seem to experience
a great deal of difficulty
finding the Asian Branch though.
So Miranda decided to
join the Black Order.
Then I look forward to
fighting alongside her, too.
That reminds me.
There's something in your
room you're going to need
to take with you before you
return to the battlefield.
Uh?
[ALLEN]
A new Exorcist coat.
It's been a long time since
I put one of these on.
Too long.
[ALL sigh]
Finally...
You guys are doing
a bang up job!
But, I have a new challenge
for you three.
[ALL]
Huh?!
What's left?!
We need to develop a Golem
that can withstand conditions
inside the Ark.
A new Golem?
What's wrong with the
one's we always use?
You tell me!
They're all toast.
[BAK] Looks like our Golems
aren't reinforced enough
to make the journey.
Sorry, Chief.
We're brainstorming a
new model as we speak.
No need for that.
I've developed a two-way
communicator we can use.
[ALL sigh]
That was close!
[BAK] Did you finish with
the data collection?
Yes! We're just waiting
on headquarters
to make their decision.
[KOMUI]
Section Leader Reever.
[REEVER]
Ah!
So. What do you think?
[clears throat] I've
examined the data.
And...?
And I can't recommend
that Allen board the Ark.
Why not?
The evidence doesn't
100% conclude
that it's the real Noah's Ark.
[KOMUI] But the Akuma
that Allen fought traveled
to the Asian Branch from Edo
aboard this, did he not?
[REEVER] There's no mistaking
that it's some form
of transportation
device. Even so,
there remain too many
unknown variables
to call it safe.
Knowing the Akuma,
it could be a trap!
[NO. 65]
Mm!
[KOMUI]
That's a shame.
Allen's already made
his intentions clear.
He's determined to board it
with or without my permission.
[ALL groan]
Yeah. That sounds like him.
Well, if that's the case...
Chief Bak!
[BAK]
Allen.
[ALLEN]
So, what's the verdict?
Wear this in your ear.
Uh...
It's a wireless communication
device we've been developing.
You'll keep in touch with
headquarters through this.
[KOMUI]
Why hello there, stranger.
Can you hear me?
Hey, Komui!
[KOMUI]
It's been a minute!
What did you find out?
[KOMUI]
Right to the chase. Very well.
My job's to make sure you
don't endanger yourself.
[ALLEN]
What? Is something wrong?
[SCIENCE SECTION gasping]
Did you hear that? It's Allen!
[REEVER sobs]
Thank God he's alive.
Aw. Section Leader
Reever. Don't cry.
[ALLEN] You're telling me
I shouldn't ride the Ark.
It's risky.
[ALLEN]
I don't care!
And I know nothing I say
is going to stop you.
So we'll compromise and
explore the Ark together.
Huh?
[KOMUI]
If we decide it's unsafe,
you're to get out immediately.
I... I'm not running away
if things get dangerous!
[laughs] Reckless
as ever, I see.
After everything, you haven't
changed one bit.
But don't forget, you're very
important to us, Allen Walker.
And we don't want anything
to happen to you.
Camaraderie isn't
a one-way street.
Honestly, don't you
care about our feelings?
[ALLEN growls]
Fine. We'll do it your way.
Tell everyone back
at Headquarters
I'm thinking about them.
It's my home.
And I'm comin' back there soon.
I promise.
You better.
Right! Let's get started.
Well you heard the man!
[ALLEN]
Wait.
I need to do something.
[KOMUI]
Oh?
[ALLEN]
Say goodbye.
To someone who can't be here.
I wouldn't be alive
if it wasn't for her.
[gasps]
How're you feeling Fo?
[FO]
So-so, I guess.
[ALLEN]
Really?
You sound better.
[FO] Resting in here
will allow me to heal.
But recuperating is such
a bore. As you know.
I'll just have to say farewell
to that crazy
Exorcist from here.
You're mean. C'mon,
I'm not that crazy, am I?
[FO laughs]
You dummy.
You care about the Akuma
as much as humans.
That's makes you
crazy in my book.
[ALLEN grunts, laughs]
[FO]
I'm tired. And need to rest.
But someone like you should
hurry back to the battlefield!
Someone like you.
[ALLEN]
See you around.
Sorry for the wait.
[BAK]
Did you finish saying goodbye?
[ALLEN]
Yes. I did.
I'm going.
Yes.
I thought Lo Fwa and the
others would be here.
It must have been too hard for
them to say goodbye in person.
Will you tell them
thank you for me?
There's no way I can repay them
for everything they did.
Of course.
We'll make sure they
get your message.
[LO FWA]
Wait! Don't go!
You can't leave yet!
Hey you guys!
Where were you?
You almost missed me.
A present!
Since your deck was missing
the Ace of Spades,
the three of us made you a new
one! It's an exact replica!
Right down to the ink!
Ha! Thank you.
Please, be careful!
See ya.
[ALLEN]
You bet.
[gasps]
[footsteps]
[BAK]
Walker!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
You made a promise!
You better come back to us!
[ALLEN]
I'm finally going back.
Back to my friends.
[TYKI]
He's still alive, you know.
In fact, he might even
be here shortly.
However,
if you die,
it'll just be us to greet
him when he arrives.
Yeah?
Guess our only choice
is to survive.
We have to be here
when Allen returns.
Otherwise, there won't be anyone
left alive to greet him.
Glad to hear.
Then I trust you'll put up
a struggle before dying.
Here we come! [yells]
[ALLEN]
The battle against the Noah Clan
continues to rage in Edo.
And as if Akuma spread across
the land and sky weren't
trouble enough,
they merge to create
an even more powerful
and grotesque form.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"Showdown in the Capital."
Bring salvation to this
poor Akuma's soul.
And, who are you?
My name's Lo Fwa!
I'm Li Kei.
I'm Shifu.
Lo Fwa. Shifu. Li Kei.
No! I'm Li Kei!
And I'm Shifu!
Ah! And I couldn't care less!
[FO]
Kanda. Admit it.
You can't memorize names.
Short Stack!
[FO laughs]
See? You don't even
remember Allen's!
[KANDA growls]
That wasn't very nice, Fo.