[SUMAN DARK roars]
[ALLEN] There's something about
the destructive force
Suman possesses.
The quantity is unusual.
Is it possible... Is the
Innocence boosting its power
by devouring his body and
shooting out that energy?
[ALLEN]
He can't go on like this.
His Innocence is killing him.
I have no choice. I have to
separate him from it.
There's no other way.
He'll lose his arm,
but at least he won't die.
It's the only choice.
I believe he would want this.
Above all else, he wants to
live! So it has to be done.
Here we go. Innocence Activate!
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN gasping]
[ALLEN groaning]
It hurts. Why does it hurt?
What's wrong?
[screams]
No. It's back up
and moving again!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[ALLEN screaming]
[ALLEN]
I heard a snapping sound,
but I don't... I don't feel it.
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN groaning]
[ALLEN grunting]
[ALLEN]
Don't do it... Suman...
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[VILLAGERS whimper]
It's coming this way!
[whimpers]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[SUMAN]
Please. I don't wanna die.
I just wanted to see my
daughter again. That's all.
[SUMAN] Someone please,
someone stop this.
[TYKI]
Well, well.
Quite the show he's
putting on. Although...
Doesn't look like he's
got too much left
in the mortality department.
[TYKI] So then. Just what will
he show us before he dies?
[LAVI yells]
I'm exhausted.
Jeez. I mean,
how many are there?
[BOOKMAN]
Mm? Is that...?
Huh?
What's happening over there?
You monster! Go back to hell!
[BOY B cries]
Wake up, Dad! Please, Dad!
[BOY B]
Dad. Please don't die! Dad!
You can't die!
I love you, Dad! No, please, no!
[JAMIE cries]
Don't go! Please, Dad!
[SUMAN DARK cries]
[BOY B]
I love you, Dad! Don't leave me!
Jamie!
[TYKI]
It looks like it's begun.
[SUMAN DARK screams]
What... What the hell
is happening?
[ALLEN grunts]
Su... man...
This... is this...?
[ALLEN]
Its body is disintegrating.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Has the last phase begun?
Does this mean that
Suman is dying?
I'm not letting
him die! [groans]
[groans] I can't move it.
It hurts too much. I've never
felt pain like this.
I'm drowning in sorrow.
I can't... fight anymore.
I can't... I can't do anything.
Uh? Timcanpy?
Ahh! What're you-- What?
Hang on, are you,
are you telling me that
you're angry with me?
Ahh! Sorry! I get it! I'm sorry!
I'll try harder!
[gasps]
Yeah, it hurts.
I'm in pain, but it's not like
I'm dead or anything, right?
So yes, I've still got it
in me to do something.
Yeah. I'll try harder.
[ALLEN]
Okay, let's go!
[screams]
Don't worry, Tim.
I'm gonna do my best.
I've gotta hurry.
[ALLEN grunting]
Hey, Suman.
[SUMAN DARK gasps]
You're... an... Ex... orcist.
That's right, my name
is Allen Walker.
It seems that... my life
is coming to an end.
I'll soon be dead. When I die,
I'll take this monster with me.
It'll die, too.
I'm sorry. I only wanted
to see my family.
I'm so deeply sorry.
Suman...
There's not much time left.
Innocence... Activate!
[screaming]
[SUMAN DARK groans]
[ALLEN]
I clearly heard my bones snap.
But at that moment,
I didn't even care.
[ALLEN groaning]
[gasping] Allen...
[ALLEN]
Suman. Listen close.
I'm gonna separate the Innocence
from your right arm.
[SUMAN DARK]
What?
[ALLEN]
Once I've fully severed it,
I'm going to pull
you out of there.
[ALLEN]
But, my arm is broken
and I don't have the
strength for it.
So you need to bite down and
latch on with your teeth.
Don't let go no matter what!
Thank you, Allen Walker.
[screaming]
No, please stop it.
You're only going to get
yourself killed as well.
[screaming continues]
It's okay. Please,
just let me go.
I don't deserve to live.
I've murdered my comrades
and so many others.
I've committed an
unforgivable sin.
A sin so grave, I can never
atone. I'm not worthy of life.
There's no salvation for me.
[ALLEN gasping]
Just live. You have to live.
[ALLEN] For all of those people
who died. You need to live.
Allen...
Don't let the darkness win.
Don't let those
lives be in vain.
Please, Suman. You have to live!
[ALLEN groaning]
[SUMAN DARK]
I want to live! I want to live!
[ALLEN screaming]
[SUMAN DARK yelling]
[ALLEN screams]
[SUMAN DARK screaming]
[BOTH scream]
Hey, Timcanpy.
[gasps] Where's Suman?
Ah! He's alive.
[ALLEN groaning]
Uh! We did it.
We severed your
Innocence, Suman!
We actually saved you,
Suman! Now you can--
Huh? Suman?
[ALLEN]
What's wrong with you?
Please, talk to me.
[gasps] Suman?
[ALLEN]
He's lifeless.
No thoughts. No reaction.
His soul... It's gone.
Oh... He may be alive,
but his soul is dead.
Why? He shouldn't be like this.
[gasps]
Hold on, this is
Suman's Innocence.
[ALLEN]
Why? Why did this happen?
[ALLEN cries]
Tell me why!
[ALLEN]
Not yet. It's not over yet.
He's not actually dead.
He is still alive.
[ALLEN]
That's all that matters.
As long as he's alive, there may
still be some hope left for him.
I wanna believe that's true.
[ALLEN]
Now, Suman.
Let's go. Let's take
you home, to your family.
[gasps]
[JAMIE] I had a dream
last night, Doctor.
I can't remember
his face very clearly,
but I'm sure it was
a dream about my dad.
It was so simple.
He just waved and smiled at me.
As if he was telling me goodbye.
My dad, he's still out
there somewhere, isn't he?
He will come back
someday, right?
[chair legs scrape]
[JAMIE]
Uh?
[DOCTOR] Of course he will,
Jamie. There's no doubt.
Goodnight now, Suman.
[ALLEN]
Too feeble to fight back,
the Noah thrusts his arm
entirely through my torso.
Smiling the whole time.
That awful feeling of his hand
on my heart, and I... I felt...
On the next D. Gray-man :
"Delete."