You. Allen!
[ALL gasp]
If it isn't Allen Walker.
I'll make you pay for this.
You won't get away!
Now, gate, open.
Heaven Compass! Get on, boy!
[yells]
[alarm blaring]
[SCIENTIST A]
Don't panic.
Maintain focus and
accuracy, all right?
I need you to check
this right away.
Yes, sir.
One would normally expect
the Branch Chief in command
to be punctual during a crisis.
[KOMUI] I'm sorry. I had a
necessary task to tend to first.
Lenalee? That task?
And where is she
during this dire time?
[KOMUI] On standby with Lavi
in one of the sickrooms.
Is that so? Standby, huh?
[KOMUI] We're under a
full-scale Akuma ambush.
There's nothing an Exorcist
deprived of their
Innocence can do.
[ROUVELIER]
Do you really believe that?
When push comes to shove...
You have to let me talk
to Hevlaska, Komui!
Experiment?
I'll beg Hevlaska.
Ask her to implant an
Innocence in my body.
I know for a fact the people
in those experiments
weren't Accomodators.
But since I am, I may be able
to respond to the Innocence
where they couldn't.
[LENALEE] And I'll be able
to save them. Everyone.
I'd be able to save
you, big brother.
[KANDA]
Komui!
Brief me on the situation.
[KOMUI]
What are you doing down here?
You're supposed
to be on standby.
You can't be serious!
[thud]
[KOMUI]
You don't have Mugen.
How the hell do you
expect to help them?
You'll be a burden!
Say that again. I'll be a what?
[KOMUI]
Follow your orders, Kanda.
[KOMUI] Please. We cannot
afford to lose you now.
Kanda!
[KOMUI]
Stay here.
You're the only active
Exorcists I've got left.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but I'm sending you in.
Using the Ark is a risk,
but Allen and Bookman
need backup.
[ALLEN yells]
[BOOKMAN]
Heaven Compass!
Pipe down! I'm working.
[SKULL B laughs]
I guess I shouldn't complain
as long as they're distracted.
[ALLEN] Just hang in there!
I'm coming for you!
Well now, lucky you. You pass.
Leave him alone!
You okay?
[SKULL B]
On!
[SCIENTIST C screaming]
Stop it!
[ALLEN]
Clown Belt!
[gasps]
[SKULL B laughing]
Dammit!
[AKUMA A laughs]
Look what I caught.
Now die.
[screams]
[BOOKMAN]
Heaven Compass!
Was I fast enough, boy?
[ALLEN]
Yeah, Bookman, thank you!
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Bookman.
[BOOKMAN] It seems I
got a little too close
to that Akuma's powers.
[AKUMA laughing]
[BOOKMAN] Looks like
this is the end for me.
I can't even bend my fingers.
[ALLEN]
Hang on!
How's it coming?
Not too much longer now.
Don't be hasty with it.
We're only gonna get
one shot at this.
Yes, sir.
Dammit.
If this keeps up, the Earl's
gonna walk away scot-free
with that egg.
[BAK] We're screwed
if we lose that egg.
It's the only way
to prevent the Earl
from creating new Akuma.
We can't let them reclaim
it no matter what.
[REEVER] Please!
Give us a little more time!
[ALLEN screams]
Ain't no one coming to
rescue you this time.
Now let's see how long it
take for your head to pop.
[ALLEN screams]
Keep fighting.
How dare you.
How dare you destroy our home.
Yeah? What exactly do you
plan on doing about it?
[AKUMA scream]
I'm putting an end
to this right now!
Didn't see that comin'.
Just as tenacious as ever.
Oh, Allen Walker.
It's time I break you.
For my Master.
The kid's really taking
control of things.
[ALLEN]
Are you okay?
Hang on, I'm coming!
[BOOKMAN]
Careful, boy.
[SCIENTIST D]
Please, get me out of here.
[ALLEN]
Uh, are you all right?
[SCIENTIST D]
I-I'm not sure. Please help me.
Well, isn't this convenient?
I'll send you both packing to
the hereafter with one ticket.
Ah! An Akuma!
[ALLEN yells]
[AKUMA B]
Not a chance!
You didn't get hit, did you?
No, you just saved my life.
Thank you very much, Allen.
You're so thoughtful.
The fact that you were fooled
by such a simple deception
goes to show you're
as soft as ever.
[ALLEN]
Lulu... Bell.
[AKUMA B] I'm gonna make sure
you suffer before you die.
Worthless Exorcist scum.
[LULU BELL]
Hold it.
This is perfect. Let's
take him home with us.
[AKUMA B]
What?
He was handpicked
by the Fourteenth
to fill the role of the Player.
I have a feeling our Master
will want to speak with him.
[AKUMA B]
Yes, ma'am.
[LULU BELL] We've recovered
the egg. Let's go.
[SKULL B]
Go on, keep it moving, c'mon.
Come along now.
You don't live here
anymore, rookies.
We're taking you all
to your new home.
Very good. That's it,
just walk right in.
I'm going ahead with Allen.
Kill the remaining
humans in the lab.
[AKUMA C]
Yes, ma'am.
They're taking him.
Well, old man, it's time
to say your final farewell.
Did you really think the two of
you alone could stop us?
[AKUMA B] What the hell?
We can't pass through!
[AKUMA C]
A barrier?
They've got talismans!
You're not taking
Allen with you!
Never underestimate
the Science Section!
[AKUMA D]
Cocky bastard!
You've only stalled us!
We'll kick through soon enough!
These makeshift talismans
won't last for long.
I'm well aware.
Dammit, Walker, wake up!
You're gonna get captured!
Please, wake up, Allen!
[BAK]
Pull it together, Walker!
Allen!
[BOOKMAN]
Come on, boy.
Wake up! Allen!
You hear that?
[LENALEE]
It's Allen!
I'm awake.
[ALLEN]
Thanks, guys.
Dammit!
Time Record! Activate!
[SKULL B]
Huh?
[MIRANDA] Enveloping target.
Time absorption. Reverse!
[SOCALO]
Not too shabby.
The Ark makes for a pretty
stylish ride, doesn't it, kid?
[SOCALO] All right, Akuma,
I'm giving you a choice.
If you got any preference
on how you wanna die,
now's the time to speak up!
It's enormous.
Holy crap!
It's a behemoth!
[SOCALO laughing]
[SOCALO]
A challenge!
Looks like it's my
lucky day after all!
[ALL gasp]
[SOCALO]
Can't you people recognize
a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity?
Well, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna go ahead
and dive right in.
[KLAUD]
Go on, it's all yours.
No objections here.
[CROSS] Unless it's filled with
booze, I couldn't care less.
[SOCALO]
Don't give me that aloof crap.
You guys just have
to play it cool.
Well, fine. More fun for me!
[SOCALO]
Torture, torture, torture!
Madness!
[SOCALO laughing]
[SOCALO] Y'know, today
feels like the perfect day
to cut loose.
[SOCALO]
Do your worst!
Amazing.
[AKUMA D]
Shouldn't you be focusing on me?
Not good!
Thanks for the workout.
Now die.
Allen!
Oh, no!
[AKUMA E] The Generals
have shown themselves!
Kill them! Kill them all!
Oh, no! There's more of them!
There's so many!
[SOCALO]
Please tell me I'm awake
'cause this is like
a dream come true.
Maker of Eden, activate!
Garden of Embrace!
[BAK]
The Garden of Embrace.
That's the Order's strongest
defense technique.
[RENI]
Well, thank goodness.
We weren't exactly handling
things so well on our own.
C'mon, quit straggling!
[SKULL B]
Hurry up and go!
They've got Tup.
Hey, Johnny!
[KLAUD] Sorry, but we're
gonna leave you here
to look after the lab techs.
Sure, fine with me.
You three can handle the rest
of the Akuma easily enough.
Well, as long as the prodigal
son hasn't gotten too rusty.
Hang on. Were you
referring to me?
[TIEDOLL] Who else would
I be talking about?
What, you want me to
prove myself to you?
You ready to come out and play?
Time for Judgment.
All right, Lau Jimin. Activate.
Lau Jimin, Anti-Akuma,
Parasite Type. Go!
Not too bad.
You're not expecting
us to do all the work.
You want me to work? Damn.
After all this time, I thought
you knew me better than that.
How would you like
it if I whipped you?
[CROSS]
Hey, I wouldn't say no.
Thanks for the motivation,
but let's save it for the
bedroom after the battle.
[grunts]
Brainless fools.
[SOCALO]
Hmm?
Cross!
Don't go tossing me your
scraps, I'm fine on my own.
[HUGE AKUMA E]
Exorcists.
[laughing]
[AKUMA E groaning]
So brutal.
[SOCALO] Like warm rain
on a spring afternoon.
[MARIE] This is Lab 5.
Come in, command center.
Noise Marie speaking.
Can you hear me?
The Akuma threat to
Headquarters has been cleared.
[ALLEN] The attack on
Headquarters persists.
Komui gives the order
to destroy the egg.
However, a mysterious
fluid floods the lab
as soon as the attack begins
and Miranda is swallowed by it.
On the next D.Gray-Man:
"The Noah of Lust."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
So beautiful!
I love summer!
I don't think fireworks are
supposed to be hurled like that.
What? Really?
No, they're not.