Hold on!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Millennium Earl speaking...
Well, that is wonderful news...!
Thanks for calling...
I'll be right over.
Another one, you say?
Well, of course!
And thank you for
calling so quickly...!
I'll wire the payment
to you right away.
Yes, yes. The
usual account it is.
Look, there's another one...!
I think that might be the
biggest lake we've seen so far!
I didn't realize there'd
be so many lakes
on this side of Liverpool...
I can't believe how
gorgeous they are...
It's no wonder they call
this area the Lake District.
People say this is one of
the most beautiful
regions in England.
Wow...! It looks great!
The last time I was
here was three years ago,
and the town square
wasn't nearly this nice...
Right, Timcanpy?
You seem happy to be back.
I am...
It almost feels like
I'm back in my hometown...
Which is a little strange since
I didn't stay here very long.
I think I know why...
This place holds a lot
of fond memories for you.
Do you think that's it?
You told me that after
you met General Cross,
things got a little
rough for you...
But I'm glad you had
some good times, as well.
I'm so excited
to meet "Mother"...
The way you've been
talking about her;
I can tell she was a good person
for you during an
important part of your life...
That's true...
She was.
Hey! You there!
You're not from
around here, are ya?
Those shoes of yours have
seen better days, am I right?
But you're in luck because
I happen to have
a brand new pair of my
famous shoes right here.
That's me.
Richard.
And I hate to toot
my own horn, but these are
the highest-quality shoes
you'll see anywhere in town.
I'm sure...
But our shoes are
just fine for right now.
Maybe next time...
Now remember...!
For the best-made shoes
in all of Liverpool,
come to Richard's Shoes!
We will...
It was a pleasure
meeting you, Richard!
You won't know pleasure
until you try on
a pair of my finest!
That place is new...
A lot's changed since
I was here the last time.
Hello there, sir...!
Those old, worn-out
shoes of yours
have seen better
days, am I right...?
What do you say we
find you a new pair?
Look at that...
He uses the same
line on everybody
that happens to
wander past his shop.
Oh...
That's the biggest building
we've seen since we arrived...
I wonder if it's a hospital.
Well, it certainly
is big enough.
We're getting closer...
Mother's house is
right on the bank
of that small lake over there.
It looks like a
funeral procession...
Oh, that poor woman walking
behind the casket...
She must be the grieving
widow of the person inside.
Everybody run...!
You're in danger!
Akuma!
Find someplace to hide...!
Get out of here!
Wh-What in the world are they?
Get as far away as
you can...! Go quickly!
Allen!
They didn't hurt you, did they?
I'm fine, but where'd
they come from?
I don't know.
I wonder if it has
anything to do with Mother?
Mother has been supporting the
Black Order for a long time.
Then we'd better
hurry up and find her.
Oh, man!
Barba!
Hey...! Allen...!
Long time, no see!
Has it really been
three whole years?
Good to see you too, Barba...
But... calm down!
Um... Allen...
Allen!
What's gotten in to you?
You'll catch a cold sleeping
on the ground...! Here.
Where's General Cross?
Did he come, too?
I'm afraid my
master's gone missing.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'll be all right...
How's Mother doing, Barba?
She's good...
She's as healthy
as she ever was...
But wait 'til she
lays eyes on you--
What is it?
Nothing...! But...
Who's this?
Oh... Sorry, how rude of me...
Barba, meet--
Mother...! It's Allen...!
Allen came back...!
And he brought his
little girlfriend with him!
So, this is your girlfriend.
I don't know what
Barba told you...
She's actually not
my girlfriend, she's--
I'm an Exorcist of the
Black Order, thank you!
I knew that.
Oh...
I didn't mean to be rude.
You're coat's a dead giveaway.
And I can't help but notice
you're wearing the
same thing, my boy.
Oh... Yes...
I've gone through my training,
and about six months ago
I was granted permission
to call myself an Exorcist.
Is that so...? That's quite
an accomplishment...
...for such a bean sprout.
A bean sprout?
So Kanda isn't the only one.
Everyone you know
thinks your short...
I can't win.
Allen...! Sure hope
you're hungry...
Look at what I made you...!
It's my special stew!
Your girlfriend will love it...!
Don't hold back, now!
I told you...
She's not my
girlfriend, she's my...
Associate! Yeah!
General Yeegar, eh?
That's right...
The Black Order
thinks it'd be best
for all available
Exorcists to split up
and protect the
other four generals...
But no one even knows
where General Cross is.
However if anyone
would be able to help us
it'd be you, so that's
why we came out here...
And what makes you think
I would know where
to find the General?
Well wait...
From what I remember weren't
you General Cross's sponsor...
That man walked out of here
leaving nothing but all
of his debt behind him...
To hell with him...
I'm sorry, but I think
I've lost my appetite.
After all you ate,
just say you're full.
I forgot to tell you...
When we were traveling here...
Lenalee and I ran into
a pack of Akuma...
I worried...
That they might have been
on there way to hurt you...
And yet here I stand without
a scratch on my head...
In all my years I've never
been attacked by an Akuma.
That's true...
But it still doesn't explain why
so many of them suddenly
appeared in the village.
Have you heard any
strange rumors lately...?
About Innocence or
anything else odd?
No, I haven't...
But I do know that
the number of Akuma
has gone up significantly
over the past six months.
If you ask me, these
things are up to something.
And in a little town like this--
I need everyone to
hurry into the next room
and keep quiet, now get going.
Why?
Is it a guest?
A little late for visitors.
Yes, dear! I'm coming!
Listen, I want you
to hear what she says,
but if there strangers here,
she won't talk to me...
So go...
Both of you, get in the other
room and keep your ears open.
Oh, and mouths shut.
Liza! Please come in!
Mother.
I know what the
director told you...
Your husband doesn't have
much time left, does he?
No... He said we should enjoy
what little time we
have left together.
But when night comes...
I don't... know what
to do with myself...
I wish there was
something I could do!
Oh, Liza...
That's only natural.
But all we can do is pray
that Lenny gets better.
When I was here before,
the villagers would
always come to Mother
when they needed
help or advice...
I guess some
things never change.
Mother says that girl
is working as a nurse
at the big hospital
in the village...
The poor thing
has a sick husband
named Lenny that's
been staying there...
But I don't think there's
much hope he'll pull through.
I can't live without Lenny...!
He's all I have left
and I don't know if
I can go on without him!
If my husband dies... I will.
You mustn't allow yourself to
think such terrible things...
He needs you to be strong...
You have to focus
your thoughts on giving
Lenny the best life you can
while you still have him...
Do you understand, dear?
I'll make sure
Liza gets home safe.
Thank you, Barba.
She's been coming over
almost every night lately...
She doesn't have
anyone else to lean on.
That worries me about her.
A person's grief
at losing someone
close to them
can be overwhelming.
And if the
Millennium Earl is able
to use that grief against her...
Which is precisely
why I want you two
to make sure
that doesn't happen.
See you when you get back!
I grew all those
flowers myself...!
You make sure they get there!
Have a wonderful day!
Ah...! The travelers
from yesterday...!
So you've changed your mind
and you've come
to order new shoes!
Well... no.
I didn't mean to put on
such a show for you two...
That'd be my
lovely wife, Sarah...
Not bad looking, huh?
Yeah...! I mean, no.
Okay...
I think we'd better go now...
Good day salesmen...
If you want another
look at Sarah,
you'll have to
try getting sick...!
Her patients at the hospital
don't know how
good they've got it!
Hospital?
I'm so sorry... my darling.
Don't be silly...
It's no trouble.
Liza, I'm so glad that
you're here with me.
All the other patients
must be so jealous.
Don't you worry about
the other patients.
The hospital director
told me I should stay here,
and that's what
I'm going to do...
He told me to think of your
care as my highest priority.
I doubt there are many
doctors in the world
who are as understanding as
the director's been with us.
If only everyone could
be as kind as that man.
Have the patient transferred
to a private room
as soon as possible.
You're kidding!
A private room...?
But Doctor...
we can't afford it!
Let me worry about the
financial side of things...
What's important now
is that we do all we can
to make your last days
with your husband
as comfortable and
peaceful as possible...
Oh, thank you...!
Thank you so very much!
The director had Lenny moved
to a special private room.
Liza has been in
there with him all day.
She's told me
all about Mother...
I assume you've both come
for her advice, as well.
That's right.
Is he serious?
If he keeps running this
hospital like a charity,
we'll be bankrupt in no time!
Get out of my way.
Is that the director?
Oh, no...
That's only Robert...
He might be a competent doctor,
but he's also one of the
greediest men I've ever met.
And I'm not the only nurse
around here that'll say so.
Yeah...
He gives the
profession a bad name...
But the hospital
director's a wonderful man.
Lenny!
I know the taste leaves
a lot to be desired...
But try to finish it all ...
Liza, come with me please...
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry...
But he really only
has a day or two left.
All you can do is cherish
what little time you have.
Is she...
I think we should
give our friend
a few moments
to collect herself.
Hey, Sarah...?
Mother sent these
flowers for Liza,
can you make sure
that she gets them?
But... You came all this way...
I wish you could
deliver them yourself.
It's okay.
If we stayed here...
I don't think I'd
know what to say.
Look at us...
I've never felt so helpless.
Watch out!
Are you all right?
I think so.
Richard...! Watch out!
Richard!
Oh no!
He'll be fine.
Director, be honest...
How is he?
I'm sorry...
We did all we could,
but unfortunately...
Oh, Sarah! I'm so sor--
I'm fine...!
Thank you, but I'm fine.
Sarah...
There's something
we should discuss...
I'd like to try to help you get
through this difficult time...
Come, now.
Liza!
I'm not strong...
If that had been me
in Sarah's shoes...
If it was my Lenny that the
director couldn't save...
I'm scared...
If Lenny doesn't make it;
there won't be anything
left for me to live for.
Don't let yourself
think that way, Liza...
Remember what Mother told you,
and focus on making his last
days the best they can be.
Has Mother given
you advice, too?
Some.
How is she?
Not bad, considering
the circumstances...
The director is taking
good care of her;
I don't think there's
anything to worry about.
And Liza.
I know this isn't easy,
but Lenalee and
I are here for you...
I want you to remember that.
She seems better today,
now that's she's had
time to get a little rest.
She does seem a bit
calmer than she was,
but I'm still worried
about how she might react
if he takes a
turn for the worse.
Lenny!
You have to try to
hang on...! Lenny!
No way...! But how?
No, she wouldn't of...!
Not Sarah!
I don't understand!
We never let her
out of our sight!
She didn't even step foot
outside of the hospital!
The Millennium Earl doesn't
let anyone's grief go unnoticed.
I knew that!
I knew and I still
let this happen!
If only we'd been more careful,
kept a closer eye on her!
I'm sorry, Sarah...
If it wasn't for me... you never
would have turned into an Akuma!
Allen.
We have to get back
to the hospital...
Something terrible happened
and we have to
discover what it was...
The hospital?
There's got to be a
way to prevent this
from happening again!
So this is goodbye...
my darling.
No...! You have to
keep fighting, Lenny!
Please, Liza...
Say it... Just once...
say goodbye.
Good... Goodbye.
Lenny... Lenny...? Lenny!
Lenny!
Suddenly, and without warning,
hoards of Akuma began appearing
in this peaceful village...
It wasn't long before
our investigation led us
to a large hospital
in the center of town.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The One Who Sells
Souls, Part 2."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!