Lenalee's in pretty bad shape...
After she was attacked by
an Akuma she started running
a fever that's showing
no signs of letting up.
The doctor's done all he can.
You're the only one
who can help her now.
That's fine.
But get her away from
that place immediately.
Are you crazy?
I can't strain Lenalee
with a trip now.
But the two of you
are being targeted.
The reason the enemy
used a fake Lenalee
was not just an
attempt to defeat you...
Their true objective was
to split the four of you up,
which they obviously
succeeded in doing.
It's hard to fathom
Akuma dreaming up
such a brilliant strategy...
There must be someone
else behind this...
And that someone
is very cunning.
Clan of Noah?
That's who I suspect...
Since Miss Lenalee
is immobile right now,
they will most likely put
all their effort
into targeting you...
Tread carefully, Lavi.
You okay back there...
I'm fine.
Hold on.
An Akuma...
Just like the old geezer said.
I should avoid
confrontation, for her sake...
I'm sorry we can't travel
using my Big Hammer.
This gorge has too
many twists and turns.
That's okay...
I can manage just fine.
Just let me know if it
gets too hard for you.
This is about the
most indirect way
to get to where we're
meeting Bookman,
but safety is most important.
Stay here 'kay...
Get away from me you creep!
Big Hammer, Little Hammer!
Grow, grow, GROW!
Hey are you alright?
Ow that thing smashed my nose...
And now my chest is flat too...!
Wait it's always been like that.
Sorry, my mistake.
Looks like you're doing fine.
Oh, Mister, thank you so
much for saving my life!!
Is there anything at all
I can do to repay you...?
Thanks to you my life, my nose,
and my chest are all okay!
You wanna go with us?
Yeah!
I've always heard its more
fun to have a travel companion!
Besides we're going
the same direction
'till we exit the gorge...
Come on, my name's
Mimi and I'm harmless.
Whaddaya say?
No, absolutely not...
Going with us will get
you into more trouble.
But I'm scared and fragile...
I have to run an errand
in the town up ahead
and I don't want
to go by myself...
Please sir, I need
you to protect me...
She obviously won't
take no for an answer...
What harm could it do?
Fine then...
But once we leave this
gorge we'll separate.
Oh thank you, thank you...!
As a maid I'll devote myself
with all my heart, nose,
and chest in serving you!
Hey... Easy.
Piece of cake.
I was able to infiltrate them
by sacrificing only one Akuma.
Everything's going exactly
to Lulu Bell's plan.
We were finally able to
weaken one of the Exorcists.
Perhaps it would be smart
to take care of her first.
If we kill the weak one first,
the other would be on his guard.
The longer she's
alive the more of
a hindrance she'll be,
making them both easy prey.
Oh I see...
But how is that so...?
Fighting just one
Exorcist is really hard.
Then make it so that
they are unable to fight.
Of course...
We're going to steal their
Innocence, aren't we...?!
Hah... Good thinkin' Lulu Bell!
Can I help?
I can carry a bag for you!
Thanks but I think
we can manage just fine.
Oh don't be silly...
Here, I'll fan for you,
how 'bout that?
Lenalee could use
it more than me.
Okay!
Thank you.
I don't mean to pry but
you don't look so well...
Maybe it would be best
if we all stopped here
and took a break...
No, I'll be alright.
Let's take a minute here...
Tip toe...
Tippy toe...
What are you doing...
I just...
I just wanted to get
my handkerchief wet...
I'm sorry I guess
I shouldn't have done that.
Trust me...
Not as sorry as I am.
It's not gonna be
as easy as I'd hoped.
I slipped and now I'm all wet!
Geez... be careful.
Lulu Bell! I did it! I did it!
Aw man, I'm soaking wet.
Time for a change of plans.
Hey Mister Lavi, I got
some dinner up for you...
I didn't ask for any.
Believe it or not,
this is my first attempt
at cooking for a man.
Huh?
You know how this works.
First I cook for you
and then we're dating
and then before you know
it we're married with kids.
Now what in the world
would I do if that happened?
It won't happen.
Please eat it, for our
future kid's sake!
I've totally got his guard down!
Now!
Extend!
Oh no!
This time for sure!
What is it this time?
I was trying to pick a flower
for your sick friend but
as soon as I grabbed it
I lost my footing and
now I can't get down!
You're unbelievable...
I'll be right there.
He fell for it!
The moment he reaches
me on the handle
of his hammer I'll jump off
and steal his Innocence!
Yeah...
Extend!
No...
How can this be happening to me?
I failed again...
If I had known it
would be this difficult
I would've asked
Lulu Bell for advice.
Come on, now's not the time
to get down on yourself, Mimi...
I'm gonna have to find
a way to make this work!
Just you wait and
see, Lulu Bell...!
I'm doing this all for you!
To make you smile!
Even though she's been resting
all this time her
fever has gotten worse
and she's showing no
signs of improvement.
Here's some water.
Thanks...
I wonder if Allen and
Krory are doing okay.
Huh?
If only I had been a little
more careful out there...
I would've never
been dragged away
by that Akuma and
we'd all still be together.
Lavi...
I know that I must have caused
you quite a bit of trouble...
I can't tell you
how sorry I am...
No...
Don't waste your energy
worrying about them,
I'm sure they're doing fine.
Seriously...
If I become any more of a burden
to you just leave
me here and go...
I don't wanna hold you back.
Even if I had to die...
Promise me that you
won't be sad okay...
I'm going to take
you to Bookman, okay...
No matter what happens...
I won't leave you.
Look I don't want
to lose you, not ever.
I won't leave your side.
No matter what it
takes, I will save you.
Lavi.
She's asking you
to leave her here,
so why not obey her wishes?
There's no point in
going through the trouble
of taking her when she
doesn't want to be taken...
Being kind in the
face of adversity
doesn't always benefit
others, you know.
Mimi.
Oh, please forgive me!
I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have said all that...
I must be getting tired!
I think I'll go rinse my face!
I wonder why
I feel so irritated.
Once upon a time in
a land far from here,
there lived a
beautiful princess...
The princess trusted her maid
more than anyone in the world...
so much so that she would
ask her opinion on everything.
The maid was loyal and
served the princess well,
living up to that level
of trust between them.
But one day, the maid
suddenly died of an illness...
So the saddened and
distraught princess
signed a contract with me,
the Millennium Earl,
to bring her reliant
friend back to life.
Kill her and wear
her body as your own!
The maid regained her
life by killing the princess
and taking on her skin,
wearing it with pride
as if it were a brand new dress.
Once upon a time in
a land far from here,
there lived a
beautiful princess.
And within her body lies
the soul of her maid
where they both live
in glorious harmony...
...as an Akuma.
Was that... me...?
I don't get it...!
Why can't I remember anything?!
That's not important now...
She's all that matters...
Madame Lulu Bell.
The days when
I would kill humans
in monotonous repetition
changed when I met Lulu Bell.
Sure, all she wanted
was for someone
to tend to her fingernails
at her beck and call...
but the idea of a person
wanting me to serve them...
of someone needing me...
made me feel good.
From that moment on,
I decided to devote myself
to being Lulu Bell's
personal maid...
And all this time I've
never once seen her smile.
That's why  I'm determined
to make this plan succeed...
I have to make her happy...
I'm sorry.
It's no sweat...
It's a lot better than carrying
the old panda on my back.
Her breathing's
become more shallow
and her pulse is weakening.
I better pick up the pace.
It looks like
it's about to rain.
Rainwater's leaking
from the wall.
Soil must be weak here.
Mimi! Run!
We have to hurry!
Lavi...
Just go on without me.
Lenalee!
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me...
Just hang in there...
Mimi!
Looks like someone
lost his Innocence!
So you are my enemy?!
You should be careful...
Letting your guard down
when you're tired...
Catch!
Too bad for you...
Your Innocence will
now be destroyed
by the one and only Lulu Bell.
Noah!
Now... it's time for the
maid to clean up the mess.
These fans are very efficient
at cutting, you know.
It's useless to run!
There's no escaping my fans!
All I want is to see Lulu
Bell smile just one time...
That can only
happen if you die!!
Lavi.
Please save yourself...
For me...
Just go...
I couldn't live with myself
if you died 'cause of me.
No way.
Resisting won't
do you any good...!
You're both going to die no
matter what you try to pull!
Why does this feel so wrong?
Don't worry Mimi, this feeling
will be gone as soon as
you kill these Exorcists!
Innocence activate.
Clean up is complete...
I'm sure Madame Lulu Bell
will be more than
pleased with these results.
So tell me how does it feel
to be attacked by
your very own weapon?
How'd you get above me?!
You used her innocence.
I can't believe she still
had enough energy to do that.
Your luck has now
run out Exorcists!
Prepare to die.
Bookman!
How dare you?!
I almost had them!!
Shame on you for falling
into the enemy's trap.
I need to treat her immediately.
You can settle this, right?
My hammer...
Consider yourself
lucky that I happened
to run into the Akuma
who was holding it.
You can lecture me later, panda!
Stamp! Fire circle!
Finish her.
I let her get away.
I can't believe I failed...
and I was so close too...
Oh, this is horrible...
I guess I'll have to wait longer
to see Madame Lulu Bell smile.
I'm done with the treatment.
Now we must wait for your energy
to come back, Miss Lenalee.
Thank you for saving me.
Geezer...
Watch her, okay...
I need to go lie
down for a bit...
Lavi.
Thank you for not
leaving me behind.
I really appreciate it.
Trying to act all macho,
it's pathetic really.
It's okay...
I just wanted him to
know how grateful I am.
That's great!
Lenalee and Lavi are
going to be alright?
Since the Akuma went
and destroyed the bridge
we were trying to cross...
Krory and I had to take
the long way around.
So... where exactly are
we meeting up with them?
I am so sorry Lulu Bell.
So... are you...
going to uh... fire me?!
I deserve my punishment.
Madame Lulu Bell...
Does this mean
I'm still your maid
and you're not
going to fire me?!
It takes a lot of
time and effort
to find a maid who is
willing to tend to my nails.
I'm going to make your nails
shine like the stars
in the sky, I promise!
Kanda and the others
arrive at an old house
where Akuma hide
in the shadows...
However, countless traps
lie in wait for the Exorcists...
On the next episode of
D. Gray-man: "Strange Mansion."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.