Romania?
Here...! This should help.
Well, what sort of
assignment is it?
We're trying to find someone...
And we have good
reason to believe
that he spent some
time in this village...
You are to
investigate the reports
and help us locate
his whereabouts.
But sir, this sort of thing
isn't normally an
Exorcist's job, right Chief?
You are correct, missing persons
are not usually
duties of Exorcists,
however, in this case,
I must say that this is
a job only for you, Allen.
Really...?
But why me...
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, noooo!
Come now, you're the
only one who can do it...!
It makes perfect
sense, don't you see?
Good Luck...
Have fun!
No...! Absolutely not...!
I won't do it, I woooooon't!
I don't want to see Master!
It's getting close.
Was that...?
It's fast!
Smell that?
Yes, I can...
It's like a kind of sweetness.
He... He got Franz!
What happened?
He took Franz over there...
Look!
What?
It... It's him!
No way!
That's him?!
It's Count Arystar Krory!
So he's... not an Akuma.
Oh yeah...
That'd be a vampire...
Agreed...
He's a vampire!
You see, this is why I didn't
wanna look for Master!
This can't be real.
I don't want to die!!
What are we gonna do?
I don't know but if possible
I'd rather not fight him.
Well, we can't let him
continue to kill the villagers,
so I'm afraid we don't have
much of a choice here, Lavi.
Okay...
Then let's do it...
Innocence Activate!
Am I to understand that you're
actually going to fight me...?
How very brave of you.
Hey, remember if you
get bitten or something...
You and I are through...
That goes both ways.
He's fast!
No, you don't!
Come on, what's
the matter with you?!
He wasn't moving
that fast before!
Big Hammer, Little Hammer!
Grow... Grow... Grow...
GROW!!!
Take that!
Holy crap, this guy has
some crazy teeth, doesn't he!
I've got you.
Stop fighting now and
you won't be harmed.
What strange little brats...
To think that you've
faced me head on
and are still able
to draw breath.
You must be monsters as well...
Aren't you?
Not exactly... you're
fighting Exorcists.
Really...?
Exorcists... Fascinating...
What do you taste like...?
Let's find out!
No way...!
He's biting my
Anti-Akuma Weapon!
Oh dammit Allen, he's...
...he's... got your blood!
Why does this blood
burn so badly?!?!!
Hey, don't go!
I warned ya...
But...
Ah... Welcome home... Arystar.
Is something the matter, dear?
Eliade, I...
I don't want you...
to ever hate me.
Hate you?
Because of, what, I've done,
I've became a vampire again.
Hello...?
Hello?!
Oh... God...
Oh, please tell me
that you're still alive...
Please...
Hello...?
Oh, please...
I'm afraid it's
too late, Arystar.
This man has
already passed away.
Don't worry--I'll bury the
body in the usual place.
How did I turn
into this monster...?!
How?!
A mob of men from the village
were just here to fight
me in the garden...
I've now become
an enemy to them,
something to be
hated, and despised.
Oh, Eliade!
How they feel can't be helped...
Don't you see, Arystar...?
They are human,
and you are a vampire.
Stay back...
Don't come any
closer to me, please!
What's the matter, Arystar?
Eliade, I...
Please don't. I will...
I will kill... you...
I know it...
Oh, God help me...
I... will...
...even though, I love you.
Don't you know
I love you, too...?
Arystar, my darling...
Don't worry yourself
with what those
people think of you...
You're above them...
My dearest Eliade...
I will love you...
with all that I have...
Let's live here in this castle
forever, you and I alone.
Yes...
Forever... and ever...
The brave Black Clergymen
have driven back the
vampire, Arystar Krory!
May God bless these brave
fighters...! Come, men...!
Hip Hip Hurray!
It would seem that
victory is upon us tonight!
But then, excuse me...
Um, why do you all seem to be
standing so far away from me?
Just giving you
space, black monk!
It's because they know
you were bitten by Krory,
and they're afraid you're going
to turn into a blood-sucker...
What?
Ah, it's crazy, isn't it?!
You see, I'm not
worried at all!
He's worried...
Oh, he's totally worried!
Come on, we should hurry
and get back to the castle,
that is, if you aren't
too afraid of me...
Why the rush?
Because the Count
abducted a villager,
that's why, remember...?
He could still be
alive in there...
Krory always takes his
victims inside the castle...!
And they never come out...!
It's happened every time!
I get it...
But, you're right, if there's
even the smallest chance...
Mayor, we want to ask you
and all of your
men to wait here...
We're going in to
investigate the castle!
Oh, don't worry...!
We now know that when
humans fight monsters,
it's far too easy for
us to lose our lives!
We shall leave it to the monks!!
So then, does he mean,
we're monsters, too?
Ahhh... I don't feel good.
Hmmm...
I see, yes, that would
explain quite a bit...
You're nothing if not
prepared, Chief Komui.
I'm impressed that you
guessed our involvement...
Remind me never to
underestimate you, Bookman.
Well, sir, we tend to
take a special interest
in our young friend
with the white hair.
You mean Hevlaska's prophecy...?
Hmm, well again, it's a
comfort that you're there.
I'm glad you're comforted
while I'm babysitting.
Yes, I see...!
I did not know that...!
Yes, yes...
Give it up, Chief...
We all know that whoever
you were just talking to
has hung up, you're
obviously faking it.
Section Leader
Reever, coffee now!
But first we need you
to approve this work!
Come now, you know
I can't concentrate
without my coffee!
That's it!
You are completely insane!
Leave me alone...!
Wow...
My brother's a mess.
"Botanical of the
Ancient," what is this?
Lavi and Allen should have
no problem taking care of it.
Seriously, we're
Exorcists--what business
do we have dealing
with a vampire?
I don't know...
What do you suppose
brought my Master here?
And don't you think it's strange
that he'd leave a
message like that...
like he knew we'd come
to help these people?
I have to wonder
if this vampire case
and my master are connected.
Of course they are...
If not, then why
are we even here?
Hey, do you smell something...?
Lavi...?
Oh!
I've smelled this before...
Lavi, wake up!
We're in trouble!
Activate!
Those flowers are
carnivorous...!
That explains all of the gas--
Lavi!
Are you alright, Lavi? Wake up!
There are too many of
them, come on, Lavi...!
Listen... You have to wake up
and help me with this!
What are you doing...?!
Stop this at once!
You wouldn't be trying
to destroy Arystar's
precious flowers, would you?!
Hmm...
Suddenly, I feel the
lusty eyes of a stranger...
Hi.
Oh my God, she's gorgeous!
Oh my.
Wow!
Lavi?!
She's totally my type and
she's looking right at me...!
Hey, Lavi, look out!
Such a handsome boy...
So, would you
like to be my lover?
Would I...?!
Yes... please...
Yes, yes, yes--
What are you
trying to do to me?!
How can you be such an idiot
over a girl like that...?
Did you happen to notice that
we're about to be eaten here?!
Allen, you are such a child.
What do you mean
"a girl like that," huh?!
That crest...
Are they really Exorcists?
My name is Eliade...
and I'm Arystar's assistant.
Now I'd appreciate
you telling me
what sort of business has
brought you here to our castle.
Sure, it's about the vampire!
We've come to
search these premises
for the villager
taken by the Count.
Oh, a villager's here...?
Hmm... Really.
I wonder if you two
can guess what this is...
Uh...
It's a coffin.
Silly boy...
I meant what do
you think is in it...
Why don't you... have a look!
Franz!
This is really bad!
Let's go... C'mon!
What... What is happening?!
Oh... Look...!
The black clergymen are
destroying Krory's castle!
Fight, Clergymen, fight...!
Yeah!
It may be...
That sending them off alone...
...wasn't the best idea.
We are so amazing...
Oh man, I thought
we were dead for sure.
What's really
amazing is this coat.
I... I don't feel so good...
Hey... what's that?!
A graveyard!
Well, these graves don't
look very nice, do they...?
You think they were pets?
I think...
it's possible we may have found
the missing villagers, Lavi.
Huh?
Think about it...
...that Eliade woman had Franz's
body in a coffin, didn't she...?
That could mean
that she was bringing
it here to bury.
Let's see, there are,
eight graves...
Yes, that would match
the number of victims
the mayor told us about.
Hmm...
but Krory killed
nine people, didn't he?
That's right, but remember,
didn't they say something about
the first woman evaporating
after he sucked her blood?
So these... are probably...
Aaaahh! You broke it!
No-No! I barely touched
it, I promise, see?!
What is that!
Hey, come here and
take a look at this!
There!
Pentacles... on the
surface of the ground.
No mistake...
Traces of Akuma blood.
Agreed...
Could this be a
graveyard for... for Akuma?
Allen, the pentacles are
showing on this one, too!
I'm afraid we're going
to find the pentacles
on every one of these graves.
Hey...
Remember when those
flowers ate Franz earlier...?
Did you see the...?
Yeah.
I saw them, the pentacles.
So then... do you think...?
The flowers... ate an Akuma?
I don't know... but I do think
there's a lot more going
on here than vampires.
The truth is beginning
to show itself,
the story of Krory, the vampire
and Eliade, the
mysterious woman by his side.
On the next episode of
D. Gray-man: "Krory Attacks."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!