What in the world...
I'm sorry everyone...
Excuse me...
Goodness...
Tag, you're it!
I'm so sorry about this...
Please say you'll forgive me.
Oh don't tell me I'm lost...
Where is the Black Order?
What...? We were expecting
Miranda hours ago.
Well, she is quite late.
It has been awhile since
the Finder was on her trail.
It could be cause for concern.
Lenalee, now that you're back,
why don't we sit down together,
have some cake and relax?
Toma...
Does she even know
where the Order is?
We gave her a map with
outlined instructions...
Based on the information
we've received
from Finders who've
spotted her in the area...
I've canvassed all
these regions here,
unfortunately,
I've come up empty.
That poor woman
is all turned around.
Guys... This is a world map...
She can't get anymore lost.
What's going on in the world?
Is it just me or have lots of
people been getting lost lately?
Now I'm worried...
It could take her
upwards of a year
to find the Order
at such a slow pace...
It sounds hopeless.
Tell you what...
I'll go see if
I can track her down.
Wait...! You don't have
to leave now, do you...?!
You haven't even had any cake!
I made it just for you!
I'll never reach the
Black Order at this rate.
I left my hometown
to become an Exorcist,
but I don't even think I could
find my way back there...
I guess life could be worse.
At least I don't have to repeat
the same day over
and over anymore...
I hope I don't have
to keep wandering
forever until I'm dead!
Maybe I should ask that
man for directions... but...
Don't talk about the following:
the Black Order and Innocence,
whether you're about
to become an Exorcist,
and anything having to do
with an official assignment.
That's right.
I need to find the
Order on my own.
It's the first test of the job;
don't screw it up, Miranda!
Watch it, lady!
Oh... I'm sorry.
My wallet's gone!
Stop him...! Pickpocket!
Lady, are you alright?
You fell down.
This is the first time I've
traveled outside my home town...
Unfortunately I don't
know left from right...
I'm sorry.
Oh, don't worry about it...
We're heading in
practically the same direction
you are so it's no big deal.
We're leaving London
just like you are.
We hope we can find a simpler
life out in the country.
Yeah...
Right, mommy...? Right daddy?
That is right, honey.
I'm sorry to hear about
your troubles in our city...
Getting lost and robbed in
the same day isn't fun at all...
Well, uh...
No, not really...
I'm used to feeling this way.
Heck a group of kids
made a song for me...
It went Miranda, Miranda...
She is the bringer
of such bad luck...
Full of doom and gloom and
misery, what an ugly duck...!
Looking for a job today,
who even cares, you'll
just get chucked...!
Like that.
Why, that's terrible, Miss.
You've had a tough life
for someone your age.
It's not... that bad.
So uh... what's
the big clock for?
Oh, well it's my
prized possession.
And, I wouldn't give
it up for anything...
I guess that thing's really
important to you, huh?
It is...
Although I also
use it for my job.
What's your job?
I'm really sorry but...
I can't tell you...
Is it a secret job?
Kids! Stop nosing
around in her business.
You don't need to know
every single detail.
That especially applies to you
because I've seen you do things
you could never tell
the children about.
What on earth are
you talking about?
That's a bold lie
and you know it!
I feel lucky to have found
such nice people to be with.
Come one, come all, to the
Isabella and Gary Magic Show!
Don't miss the
greatest show on earth!
Hey, Guy... Anne...
You mind, I would like
to help if you'd... let me.
We've got it all
handled, Miranda.
You don't have to.
Yup.
Oh no... Your family has
been so generous...
The least I can do is
help out wherever I can.
Why don't you go take a
break for a little while.
No way, this is my job!
Then help Anne...
I just want to pass
out flyers for an hour.
I don't need your
help with work.
Come on Guy, just
for a few minutes...
I said no!
Miranda...!
Forget about the silly flyers.
I need your help
getting everything ready
for dinner tonight.
Right... I'm sorry.
Potatoes and carrots,
skinned cleaned
and ready to go on the stove.
Miranda, Miranda...
She is the bringer
of bad luuu...
Full of doom and gloom and
misery, what an ugly duck...!
Looking for a job today,
who even cares,
you'll just get chucked!
Miranda, Miranda... she is
the bringer of bad luck...
Looking for a job today...
Fire!
What's wrong?!
Miranda!
Oh no!
I'm so sorry!
It's Miranda Lotto, right...?
Well, just be... careful.
I will.
Well, I guess
that's about it then.
Oops, you dropped this.
What's this mark?
The Black Order?
Oh, yeah, sorry...
Please don't tell anyone else.
Would you... happen to know
someone named Allen Walker?
I'm sorry, so you met Allen
when he was traveling
through town...
That's right...
He was on his way to
the Black Order place,
just like you are...
He looked suspicious,
so I questioned him on
a murder case I was on.
Does that mean you're
an Exorcist too?
Uh... Sort of.
I see.
Well, if you have a problem,
don't hesitate to contact me...
I can help.
Thank you, I appreciate it...
Miranda!
You doing better?
Oh yes...
I hope I didn't worry you.
Well then, hope you
all have a good night...
No worries.
We're just glad you're okay.
Not only did I fail to
help you, I ruined your dinner.
Don't be silly...
We have a job offer.
It's perfect for you,
if you want it.
Welcome and good evening
ladies and gentlemen!
What I'm about to show
you has never been
done before in
the history of man...
Skewering a woman alive!
I will pin her inside this box,
giving her no way to escape,
then stab the box with swords,
leaving her vulnerable
to mortal wounds.
Now any of you in the audience
who are faint of
heart should leave now.
This worked out perfectly...!
Gary's assistant just up and
quit on him a few days ago.
I wonder if she'll be okay.
I hope she'll be okay.
Without further ado...
Let us commence!
It's just magic...
Magic!
Magic, magic,
magic, magic, magic...
Welcome and good evening
ladies and gentlemen!
What I'm about to show you,
has never been done before...
Please help!
I'm so sorry,
please forgive me...
You know in my entire
life of performance,
I've never experienced a
show quite like that one...
It was stupendous...
So you're the reason
the show repeated itself...?
I take responsibility,
but it wasn't me,
it was the clock's fault.
Turning back the
hands of time...
What incredible magic...
It's something,
however everyone in
attendance, including us,
had no idea that it
was even happening.
Even though I trusted
you wouldn't hurt me,
I couldn't help myself...
I'm sorry.
No, don't be...
I shouldn't have said
anything in the first place.
You'll be heading off to
your real job tomorrow...
Don't let tonight get to you.
Good night!
What's wrong?
I don't see how someone as big
of a mess as me
could even hold a job.
If it'd make you feel better,
you can always travel
with us for the time being.
The trick will help
you get over your fears.
Well... Will you?
Well will you?!
It's true...
I don't have the skills or the
willpower to become an Exorcist.
Maybe I should travel with this
family and be in their show...
What do you think?
What is it?!
Daddy... What's wrong?
Where's the Innocence?!
What Innocence?
No!
Yes...
Come on kids!
Get inside!
Please stop...!
Don't destroy my clock!
It's all I have!
Miranda?!
Hey, Miranda...! You are
an Exorcist, aren't you?!
Destroying Akuma
is your job, isn't it?!
I'm not officially
an Exorcist yet!
I can't fight back!
I don't even know how to!
I wish Allen and Lenalee
were here to help.
You are an Accommodator
of Innocence.
All Accommodators become
Exorcists and fight Akuma.
The only way I can help
myself and my friends
is to become an Exorcist
like I had planned...
So why am I hesitating?
But I'm not capable of
destroying Akuma yet!
If they're attacking
because of my Innocence,
then I can't just sit
here and cower in fear!
Akuma... Over here...!
I've got the Innocence!
Miranda!
Stop right there!
No... I can't...!
Shoot her! Right meow!
Looks like those Akuma are
trying to get your clock,
and if they are, you need
to leave it her and run...
I can't!
Hurry!
No...! I won't!
Look, if you don't come
with me you're gonna die!
I don't care!
I'm hit.
Are you okay?
Take my bicycle
and get out of here!
What about you...
You're gonna become
an Exorcist, right...?
Then you don't wanna
be killed here!
Moa...
Miranda, go!
Here goes...
I hope this works...
Please activate...
My Innocence!!
One more time.
I can't do this... anymore!
Lenalee!
Stay back!
Damn Exorcists!
You're safe now...
Are you okay?
I thought you
could use some help.
Thank you...
What's wrong?
I couldn't even find
my way to Headquarters.
You'll be fine.
You risked your own life
by drawing the Akuma's attention
away from everyone else.
With courage like that
you can be an Exorcist
and a good one too!
I agree completely...
believe me...
Thanks, Lenalee.
Thank you so much
for your hospitality.
I'm sorry for all
the trouble I caused...
You're really leaving?
It's hard to believe that
fighting those disgusting things
is what you do for a living.
You're right...
I know that now...
I will become an Exorcist.
It's probably the one thing
I'm destined to do with my life.
If there's anything I could
do to repay your kindness,
it would be to rid the
entire world of Akuma.
And to prevent honest
people like yourselves
from being put
in danger by them.
I really can't thank you enough.
And could you say
hello to Allen for me?
Moa!
No way! You know Allen?
She said he came
through this town once.
Yeah, Allen destroyed
Akuma while he was here,
and saved a lot of lives.
He also saved my sister's soul.
Good luck to you.
Thank you!
Maybe someday I can visit
as a full-fledged Exorcist,
just like Allen!
I hope I haven't caught a cold.
What...? Miranda still
hasn't arrived yet?
How could she have
gotten separated again?
While we were on our
way back we took a break,
and before we knew
it she was gone.
Mine...
Look there...
Wait a second...
Chief...! Found her...
Oh that's not good...
Wow...
I guess climbing a
massive cliff is part
of the test for
becoming an Exorcist...
Don't fall yet!
You're almost to
the top, Miranda!
Are you alright?
I'm sorry...
I can't do anything
right by myself.
Miranda, what made
you climb up that cliff?
Huh?
There's an entrance underground
from there you can take an
elevator all the way to the top.
Well you got here in one piece,
which is what matters...
Miss Lotto...
Welcome to the Black Order.
Thank you...!
Now I can really
become an Exorcist!
Stop it...!
I've changed my mind!
But how else do you expect us
to turn the Innocence
into a weapon?
Not my clock...!
I don't wanna become an
Exorcist anymore...! Stop it...
Lenalee!!!
I pass through a
port town in order
to cross the ocean
for an assignment...
I soon come to realize that
many of the ships in the port,
are being sunk by
an unknown assailant.
Next time on D. Gray-man:
"Mysterious Ghost Ship."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.