Stop this! If you damage
it anymore, it'll--!
Allen Walker!
I'll kill you for this!
You're a terrible Master.
I did it because I had
faith in you, my apprentice.
[BOOKMAN] There's no need to
worry. She's just unconscious.
What a relief.
[giggling]
[JOHNNY]
Stop. Stop it.
You... You can't!
[RENI]
This can't be happening.
This is all... It's a dream.
It's very real.
Did you think the Akuma
could be stopped so easily
by your vain efforts?
[SKULL B] They were created by
the Earl to be living weapons.
Continuously evolving. Adapting
to efforts to kill them.
Wait. Is that its level?
[JOHNNY] What have I done?
This is all my fault!
He was already dead.
If only I hadn't been stupid
and tried to save him...
[JOHNNY screams]
[JOHNNY] ...I wouldn't
have gotten caught
in the first place!
It's still alive?
Johnny!
[MARVIN]
We're gonna get you out of here!
[OFFICER A]
Just hang on, Johnny!
[JOHNNY]
Chief Bak.
They have Tup!
We're on it!
Trap those Skulls, Reni! Here!
[RENI]
You got it!
[SKULL C gasps]
Great shot! This is our chance!
Hurry up and get
away while you can!
The battery, it's dying!
Mine won't last
much longer either!
[screams]
[ALL screaming]
Damn it!
I got you!
[screams]
[JOHNNY]
What have I done?
[JOHNNY] I was so worried
about saving Tup,
I got everyone else hurt.
I dragged them all into this,
when I should've let him go!
It's my fault! I did this!
What happened here?
[MARVIN]
Allen...
Allen. Be careful.
The Akuma... it's evolved.
[MARVIN]
We tried to stop it.
I'm sorry, Allen. We failed.
[giggling]
I'm Level 4.
And what's your name?
[MARIE]
Huh?
Are you picking
something up, Marie?
Yes, it's an Akuma.
But it's frequency is-- Uh!
What's the matter?
[MARIE]
I don't know.
But I've never heard a
noise like this before.
[ALLEN]
It's soul... it's sickening.
This Akuma, I've never
seen one like it before.
One as terrible.
[ALLEN]
So this is Level 4.
It's too horrible.
I can't even look at it.
[JOHNNY]
Al... Allen.
Allen. I'm sorry.
Please help the others!
How can I?
[JOHNNY]
You have to help save everyone.
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault!
Please, Allen. Save them!
[LEVEL 4]
Who is "everyone"?
Tell me, are you crying?
[ALLEN] Yes, for those
who didn't survive,
but also for you and your soul.
But now, you're going to pay!
[yells]
I'll destroy you!
Not only for what you did,
but for your own sake!
[MARIE, BOOKMAN gasp]
A Level 4?
[ALLEN]
Bookman!
There's several injured people
over there! Please help them!
[yells]
Gotta hurry.
I have to defeat it!
Before it gets stronger!
[ALLEN] Shivers are
running down my spine.
Where's all this
fear coming from?
Is this what it's like
battling a Level 4?
Being completely
overwhelmed by dread?
[LEVEL 4] Oh, that's right.
I nearly forgot!
This place is the Headquarters
of the Black Order, isn't it?
And I am a weapon of carnage,
so I should carry
out my purpose:
To massacre every
living person in here.
[TIEDOLL]
Huh?
What's this strange
feeling I'm getting?
Coming somewhere near Gate 26?
[TIEDOLL]
Marie. Do you read me?
Yes. What's wrong?
[TIEDOLL] Is anything
happening near the Gate?
Yes, sir. An Akuma appeared.
[BOOKMAN]
It's a Level 4.
A Level 4?
Curious. Akuma are
living weapons.
Which means, it could
continue evolving.
[BOOKMAN] Despite being
mechanical soldiers,
this one's incredibly
similar to a human.
The entire 100-year
history of the war
between the Black
Order and the Akuma
has been recorded
by the Bookmen.
Countless documents
detailing the conflict.
Despite all the data,
the final form
of the Akuma remains a mystery.
Up to this point,
only three Levels
had been observed and confirmed.
In other words,
this moment is historic.
A monumental event not only
for the Black Order,
but all of mankind as well.
This is our first
contact with a Level 4.
Level 4 confirmed!
Did you say a Level 4?
[yells]
No more! You won't kill again!
Fight me!
[ALLEN]
I can't shake this uneasiness.
Even though I'm the
only one attacking,
the more I hit him,
the more it feels like
I'm somehow receiving damage.
Spiritual wounds. Feelings of
helplessness and despair.
[giggles]
[ALLEN]
Edge End activate!
Please! Tell me it worked!
[gasps]
I've decided.
I'll start with you.
[ALLEN screaming]
No! Don't hurt Allen!
[giggles]
[gasps]
It wields such
incredible power.
I lost him!
Walker....
No, Allen!
[LEVEL 4 giggles]
So who's up next?
[LEVEL 4 wailing]
[BAK screaming]
This sound!
[MARIE screams]
It's too much!
[TIEDOLL]
Marie! Marie! Are you okay?
What on earth is that noise?
No use.
This screeching is
making me too dizzy
to stay synchronized
with my Innocence!
[SOCALO]
What the hell is that sound?
Whatever it is, it's
throwing me off balance!
The damn bastard
won't stop screaming!
On! Gataru!
[CROSS]
You'll be okay, Maria.
Since you're dead,
use Carte Garde to gain
control over my body.
[LEVEL 4 giggles]
Were you gathering
humans for me to harvest?
[TIEDOLL]
Don't-Don't you dare!
[SOCALO yells]
[gasps]
Link, you saved my life.
You didn't think I'd let Allen
Walker die that easily, did you?
What...? What happened?
No. It can't be.
Where is the Science Section?
It's gone. There
isn't anything left.
Then that means...
Bookman... Marie, Miranda...
Even my master.
Everyone's gone...
[LINK]
That's impossible!
The Generals couldn't
have been defeated.
[SKULL B laughs]
[SKULL B]
Cower, you pathetic fools!
[SKULL C] You're doing
beautiful work, Level 4!
[LEVEL 4]
Hm?
Just as expected from one
of the Earl's creations!
Now get over here
and help us break free!
[SKULL C]
If we don't return soon,
we're gonna be in deep
trouble with Lord Millennium!
[SKULL B] Destroying this
barrier should be nothing
for someone as powerful as you!
[SKULL B laughing]
Huh?
[SKULL C]
Uh?
The idiot doesn't know
his own strength!
He shot right through me!
You double-crosser!
[gasps]
[LEVEL 4 giggles]
[LEVEL 4]
Sorry.
I guess I just got over-excited!
I'm so worked up,
there's no way I can calm
down until I kill even more!
I bet there are humans on
the other side of this door.
No! It's leaving!
That monster is about to
break into Headquarters!
I have to stop him.
Are you all right? Walker!
I've never seen
anything like it.
Contact the command center!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Warning!
An Akuma has entered
Headquarters from Lab 5!
But how?
[ANNOUNCER A]
Lab 5 has been destroyed!
The Akuma has escaped
beyond its walls!
I repeat!
An Akuma has annihilated Lab 5
and entered Headquarters!
Allen.
[ANNOUNCER A]
Furthermore, it appears to have
evolved to Level 4.
We haven't been able to confirm
the Exorcists' safety
inside Lab 5!
I repeat!
[LINK
Walker! Wake up!
There's no time!
You've got to get up now!
Allen! Allen!
[ALLEN ] The Level 4 escapes Lab
5, leaving a path of destruction
as it proceeds deeper
into Headquarters.
As it continues wreaking havoc,
a new target enters its sight.
On the next D.Gray-man:
"To the God I Hate So Much."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
Listen up! We have a new
transfer student, Lero!
Give Level 4 a warm welcome!
Nice to meet you.
Wait a minute. For?
Oh! Yeah! I kinda miss her!
Hey!
[LERO]
Quite the temper.