[gasps]
Where am I?
[SHADOW] Not even the
Earl knows this room.
This is the Fourteenth's
secret place.
[CROSS] No time!
Is there a piano in there?
[ALLEN]
What?
[CROSS]
A piano! Do you see one?
Yeah, it's right here.
[CROSS] Good. Then I
need you to play it.
That's the heart.
It's what controls the Ark!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
Is that... the score?
[MIRANDA]
Where's that one going?
Please, Time Record,
I'm begging you!
Stop time for Noah's Ark, now!
[MIRANDA]
Just save my comrades.
What the...? This crest is...
No. It can't be.
No way. How did these
symbols get here?
[SHADOW]
They're notes for a song.
The melody lives in
you, Allen Walker.
I can't play.
Is this the music
for these symbols?
This melody... It's familiar.
[VOICE]
♪ Fire slowly burns ♪
♪ As the boy is drifting
off to sleep... ♪
Who's voice is this
singing inside my head?
[VOICE] ♪ ...flame in the
ashes of our memories ♪
♪ Breathing in, then out again ♪
♪ There I see the face of
my precious boy appearing ♪
♪ And every dream that I
had for him him is falling ♪
♪ To the ground,
to the ground ♪
♪ Within the darkness... ♪
Come on, my stupid apprentice!
Do you hear that sound?
[VOICE]
♪ Born in the night with eyes ♪
♪ Gray and trembling,
yet so bright ♪
♪ Even if every word... ♪
That's a piano.
It's started!
Allen! Do you read me?
[VOICE] ♪ Fell to the earth
Not to be heard ♪
♪ Forgotten and
turning to dust ♪
[ALLEN, VOICE]
♪ I will still pray endlessly ♪
♪ for this young boy to... ♪
Now, Allen! Control the Ark!
Play with your heart!
Play with hope!
With my hopes?
[CROSS]
What're you waiting for?
Make a wish.
[gasps]
I wish for...
I want... the download.
For the Ark.
That's not it.
What I really want...
[KOMUI]
Nothing comes to mind?
When everyone comes back,
first thing I'll do is
welcome them home.
[KOMUI] Then I'm going to give
Lenalee a great big hug.
And after that, I'll make a
banquet of food for you to eat.
[VOICE] ♪ Fire slowly
burns as the boy... ♪
[KOMUI]
I'll throw a blanket over Lavi,
who'll fall asleep on the spot.
[VOICE] ♪ ...embers flame
in the ashes of our memories ♪
♪ Breathing in, then out again ♪
♪ There I see the face
of my precious boy... ♪
[KOMUI] For the adults,
I'd like us to toast with wine.
Have a large celebration
and fall into a slumber.
[VOICE]
♪ ...I had for him is falling ♪
♪ To the ground,
to the ground ♪
♪ Within the darkness you're
the one who's always shining ♪
♪ Born in the night with eyes ♪
♪ Gray and trembling,
yet so bright ♪
♪ Even if every word
of my endless praying ♪
♪ Fell to earth ♪
♪ Not to be heard ♪
♪ Forgotten and
turning to dust... ♪
[KOMUI] And then,
once the party's over...
...Kanda will show up,
grouchy as ever.
[VOICE]
♪ ...for this young boy ♪
♪ To one day find
love unconditional ♪
♪ And that he may be
kissed on the hand ♪
[ALLEN]
I have my wish.
Give me back all my friends!
You hear me?! Don't disappear!
This can't be possible.
The town had
completely vanished,
but it's right in front of me.
[LENALEE]
Look at the egg.
It's changing back
into its normal form.
[CROSS]
Huh.
Seems like stopping the download
also caused the termination
program to cancel.
That was a close call.
Allen, guess what. We won.
We were able to disrupt the
transfer of the factory,
preventing the Earl from
getting his hands on it.
Hell of a victory
for me. And you.
[CROSS laughs]
He's ignoring me.
Are you there, Allen?
Allen. Are you okay?
Say something!
[CROSS]
Hm.
Fine then. We'll go to the
room you're currently in.
Just create a door for us.
All you have to do
is hope for one.
[electricity popping]
[LENALEE] He knows more about
the Ark than he's letting on.
Oh, Lenalee.
I'm glad to see
you're doing okay.
You too, Allen.
I heard a piano.
Somehow it stopped the
Ark from collapsing.
Was that you playing?
It was lovely.
If there's something
you want to ask,
now's your chance, my pupil.
But do me a favor
and stop glaring.
[ALLEN]
Tell me, Master.
Why was that music in my--?
[LAVI]
Come and get it, Allen!
What the--?
[CHAOZII] Jeez, Lavi. I mean,
it's not like he's a dog.
[LAVI]
Oh, yeah? Just watch.
When I yell food, I guarantee
he'll come runnin'
wherever he is.
Come and get it, boy!
I know that voice!
hat infernal noise is coming
from inside the Ark.
You seem certain about
that, Master. How?
Better hurry before
they're gone!
Let's eat!
Are you really an Exorcist?
[LENALEE]
It's Lavi and Chaozii!
They're both alive.
[CROSS]
Hm.
Looks like you managed to
bring back the entire town.
Makes sense seeing how
it wasn't destroyed,
just stuck between dimensions.
Not like it would've
killed them or anything.
[ALLEN] Wait a minute, Master!
You said my friends were dead!
[CROSS] Hm? Well, they were
almost as good as dead.
It's practically the
same difference.
[ALLEN] You lied to me! You
said they were definitely gone!
Lavi! Can you hear us?
We're over here! We'll
find you in just a second!
Master, why can't
they hear our voices?
Don't just sit there
looking arrogant!
Give me some answers!
[CROSS]
Do shut up!
Nikujaga! Steak!
Mackerel with kimchi!
Curry, rice, and sautéed
liver with chives!
It's all yours!
[LAVI panting]
[LAVI] The bait is set. Now we
just wait for him to bite.
[CHAOZII]
Yeah. Let's wait.
[LAVI gasps]
[CHAOZII]
Uh? What is it this time?
I was just thinking. If we
survived, then that means...
Yes. It's possible.
Yu and Krory could be alive.
[LAVI]
Yu's got straight bangs!
Was that supposed to make me
find you, you dumb bunny?
Ah! Yu!
[LAVI] Is that Krorykin's you're
carryin'? He's still alive!
[KANDA] I found him
lying in another room.
What's going on?
[LAVI]
You know as much as I do!
Hey, short stack! We're all
here! What're ya waitin' for?!
[ALLEN] Don't you ever
call me that name, Lavi!
I just heard Allen's
voice! Where is he?
Where you hidin', short stack?
Call me that again,
see what happens!
The name is Allen. You idiot.
Allen! Are Lenalee
and Cross safe?
[ALLEN]
They're both here with me!
I'll send you a door that
will lead to this room.
[KRORY]
Eliade.
[LAVI] Uh! You hear that?
Krorykin's spoke!
[CHAOZII]
We're all alive! It's a miracle!
I'm so happy.
[LAVI]
This place is quiet as a tomb.
Man, how did we get
outta this mess?
So wait, were you the one who
put the Ark back to normal?
Yeah, although,
I'll admit, I'm not
sure how I did it.
Yeah. I wasn't around
to document it.
[ALLEN gasps]
It's Timcanpy!
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen him since
we split up in China.
[ALLEN]
Now, go.
t's up to you.
[ALLEN]
Since that night...
...I've just been so
busy, I'm sorry!
How I've missed you, Timcanpy!
And, look how much you've
grown since you were away!
Why have you grown?
I hate to interrupt this
touching moment, but--
[KANDA]
Can it, short stack.
The name is Allen, got it?
I've walked through every
street in this damn town,
but I never found any sign
the Noah are still here.
Hey, Kanda there's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
What's with that
tattoo on your chest?
And that symbol,
does it mean anything?
No comment.
What a great attempt
at a conversation!
But what do you say you
give it another shot?
[KANDA]
Piss off.
Just like an old married couple.
[sighs]
[KANDA] Let's cut to the chase.
How do we escape, short stack?
[ALLEN] For the last time,
it's Allen, jerk!
[LAVI] Can you stop
fighting for a second?
I'll check if we
can get out this way.
Or not.
[ALLEN screams]
[LAVI]
There's no floor!
[yelps]
[LAVI]
What? Don't grab onto me!
The hell were you
thinking, short stack?
[LAVI]
Choking! You're choking me!
I can safely say this isn't
connected to the outside.
I outta drop you, short stack!
[ALLEN]
My name's Allen.
If you're gonna fall,
do it alone!
[LAVI]
Did you hear me all right?
About the whole choking thing?
I'll lift you guys up!
[yells]
I believe in you, Chaozii!
[LAVI]
I believe I'm about to pass out.
You betray the sacrifice
they made for you!
If you save him,
then you're my enemy!
In my eyes, that makes you
no different than an Akuma!
[CHAOZII] After everything, I
still can't forgive you, Allen.
Huh?
What is that?
[gasps]
[LAVI]
I almost forgot!
You're an Accommodator, Chaozii!
And a strong one to boot!
[KANDA]
Explain.
[CHAOZII]
It's attached to my wrist.
My guess is, since the
Ark has been stabilized,
it must've allowed the
Innocence to come find you.
The power to defeat Akuma.
This Innocence is mine to wield.
A gift from Anita and the crew.
I'm sure of it.
[LAVI]
Speaking of which,
my Innocence has
seen better days,
but here's hopin' it'll
piece back together.
Looks like we're in
the same boat, Yu.
[KANDA growls]
I'm sure Komui will
fix 'em for ya.
[KANDA]
Komui is the problem.
[KOMUI laughing]
Repair them? Of course I can!
For a slight fee that is!
More importantly, I'm
worried about Count Krory
not being able to wake up.
If we don't get
outta this place,
we can't get him the
medical treatment he needs.
At least my Master and
Lenalee are watching over
and taking care of him.
Alone together.
[ALL]
Oh, no.
[LAVI] A renowned womanizer
and sweet Lenalee.
[KANDA, ALLEN]
Alone? Together?
[CROSS] Looks like he
pushed himself to the limit
during his battle.
He may be in a coma
for quite some time.
[LENALEE] Poor Krory. He got
it the worst of any of us.
It was his Innocence that saved
him by supercharging his body.
If you want him to wake up soon,
what he needs is to rest.
That's the best
thing for him now.
I'm so sorry. Sleep well, Count.
[CROSS] You're more comfortable
revealing your emotions
since I saw you last, Lenalee.
What?
[CROSS] And you've become
a beautiful woman.
I don't know about that.
But you, you're still elusive
as ever, General Cross.
My brother's been searching for
you all this time, you know.
[CROSS] The fact he let you
leave his side is shocking.
[chuckles]
Tell me, when did you
get aboard the Ark?
Remember when you were
fighting the Noah in the city?
I was nearby as well.
It was the perfect time
to sneak into the Ark,
using Maria's ability
to go unnoticed.
What a shame.
Had I only caught sight of you,
I would've revealed
myself much sooner.
What do you expect to
get from complimenting me?
It's such a pity.
Your hair was beautiful.
Your hair. It's so beautiful.
Promise me you'll
grow it long again.
Don't let this war beat you.
It's kinda strange.
Anita said those exact
same words to me.
I understand.
I told her not to follow me
no matter what happened.
She was devoted.
And a fine woman.
General.
Please make me a promise.
Protect my Cross.
[ALLEN, LAVI gasp]
[gasps]
[screams]
[ALLEN]
Master! That's a crime!
[LAVI]
If only we'd gotten here sooner!
[LENALEE] What? No. It's not
like that, Allen. We were just--
[CROSS] She's 16! A full-fledged
woman! So stop raving, idiot!
[ALLEN]
Have you no decency?
[LENALEE]
General! You're embarrassing me.
[CROSS]
The real crime is you leaving
this beautiful girl alone,
stupid apprentice!
[LAVI]
Lenalee,
are you sure nothing
happened between you two?
[CHAOZII] You Exorcists are
embarrassing to be around!
[LENALEE] Hold on. What do
you guys think happened?
[ALLEN] All I know is that
it's a crime, Master.
--[ALLEN] A serious crime.
--[KANDA] Oh, who cares?
Sweet Eliade.
[ALLEN]
Our arduous journey concludes
and we arrive home at the
headquarters of the Black Order
for a long overdue
reunion between friends.
However, our feelings
of joy are short lived
as dark clouds loom
on the horizon.
On the next D.Gray-man:
"Homecoming"!
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
Hey, Lavi. Who were you
saying has short bangs?
You mean Kanda!
[KANDA]
Yeah? That so, eye patch?
[LAVI]
Huh? Wait a minute!
[KANDA]
Mugen! Unsheathe!
[KRORY]
You guys are too noisy.
I was in the middle
of a great dream.
Krorykins is awake!
Are any of you even
listening to my lecture?
Anyone?