♪
[KANDA grunts]
[KANDA]
Dammit!
My left hand doesn't
feel the cold anymore.
And my knees.
They're numb as well.
[KANDA grunts] I won the fight,
but damn, must have drained too
much of my lifeforce
in the process.
Now my recovery
time's at a crawl.
[KANDA gasps]
Remember you're not immortal.
Don't overestimate how
much life you have.
[grunts]
[KANDA] I feel like I'm going
to pass out. How pathetic.
This is no time for weakness!
Okay! I'll stay
behind too! Bye guys!
Kanda!
Make sure you catch up with us
really soon, okay? Be careful.
[grunts]
[KANDA] My mind's slipping,
flooded with pointless memories.
Maybe someday I'll die. But not
now and not in this place!
[ROAD] The Lord saw how
great the wickedness of the
human race had
become on the earth.
And that every intent of the
thoughts of their heart
was only evil continually.
[ROAD]
And the Lord was sorry.
Regretful he had made
human beings on the earth.
The grief was so strong it
struck deep in His heart.
So then God proclaimed,
"I will blot out from
the face of the earth
the very human race
that I have created.
From man, to animals, the birds
and the creatures that move
along the ground.
None will be spared."
[SKINN] Never forgive.
Never forgive the Innocence!
[ROAD]
"I will destroy them all,
for I'm sorry that
I have made them."
Noah, eh?
[SKINN grunts]
[PRIEST A] Well, that was the
name of the man from the
Old Testament responsible
for building the Ark.
I'm sorry. You are?
The name's Skinn Bolic.
I'm a laborer employed
over at the shipyards.
Well, please to meet you, Skinn.
I work for--
[SKINN] The Church.
You're a priest, aren't you?
That's right.
So, what spurred
this interest in Noah?
[SKINN] Something's wrong
with my body lately.
My head's been bleeding.
What? Bleeding?
You need to see a doctor
instead of a priest, my son!
[SKINN]
Can't afford it.
If you could just
take a look, Father.
What could I possibly tell you?
[gasps]
[PRIEST A] That... That mark!
It's... Stigmata!
[SKINN grunts]
[PRIEST A]
Are you alright?
Is this mark causing
you that much pain?
Someone! Help me
move him inside!
[SKINN grunts]
[SKINN] In my 25th year,
on a cold Autumn day,
My old life ended and my
awakening as a Noah began.
[PRIEST A pants]
Quickly, Father!
His condition's bad!
[SKINN screams]
You must be strong!
Ask God for help!
[SKINN] It hurts!
My body hurts all over!
Help me! Someone stop the pain!
It's unbearable!
[screams]
[PRIEST A] Bring a
sedative and holy water!
[NUN A]
Yes, Father!
I know it hurts. But you
must fight the pain!
I can't!
[screaming continues]
[ROAD] Every living thing
that moved over the earth
was destroyed. From the birds,
to the livestock, wild animals,
the creatures that live
and swarm over the land.
And among them this included,
naturally, all of mankind.
[SKINN] The excruciating pain
was always followed by the
same visions.
Dark and terrifying
dreams of the Apocalypse.
Then the stirring of a presence,
long dormant,
awakening inside me.
[ROAD] And when God had
concluded his work,
everything on dry land that had
at one point drawn the breath
of life through its nostrils,
had uttered its final gasp.
Every living thing on the face
of the earth was extinguished.
The people and animals.
From the creatures that
move along the ground,
to the birds that
nest in the trees.
All were wiped from the earth.
And none survived.
[SKINN grunts]
Never forgive it.
Never forgive.
Never, never forgive.
Never forgive it.
Never forgive it. Never forgive.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Aw, look at this poor boy.
He just can't seem
to get any sleep.
And so, only Noah was left,
and those who were invited
aboard the Ark before the rains
flooded the earth etcetera...
There's more,
but who has the time?
[SKINN grunting]
Noah's animosity is still
as strong as ever.
Even after 7,000 years.
[grunting continues]
[ROAD] Instead of chewing your
fingers, how about some candy?
I promise it's sweet.
[SKINN grunts]
[ROAD]
There now. I knew you'd like it.
[grunting]
Skinn Bolic, my boy. Time to
embrace your true form
as one of the 13 Children
of God. An apostle with
the blood of the Noah clan
coursing through your veins.
[gasping]
Wondering why you're
experiencing these feelings
of hatred and sadness?
Echoes of events that transpired
several millennia ago.
So tragic, they're forever
burnt into your genes.
Dear brother.
The memory you carry etched
into your flesh, is anger.
All this anger.
I'm so proud.
Your awakening is complete.
And now that your
eyes are wide open,
you can see the true colors
of this world, can't you?
[whimpers]
[SKINN, MILLENNIUM EARL sob]
[ROAD]
There, there.
[sobbing continues]
So you're up. Looks like
your strength has returned.
I'll prepare you a
breakfast right away.
Been some time
since your last meal.
You must be starving.
[SKINN]
Hey.
Father, I'm going home.
By tomorrow, anyone who knows me
from the shipyard or the church,
wipe them from the
face of the earth.
As you wish, Lord Noah.
It shall be done.
--[SKINN grunts]
--[door clatters]
[SKINN]
Never forgive it.
Never forgive.
Never forgive...
Never... Never.
Never. Never. Never!
Never forgive! Never forgive it.
No matter what happens,
never forgive God!
Never forgive it!
No matter how many years pass,
never forgive what has happened!
[SKINN]
Never forgive the Exorcists.
Never forgive Innocence.
Never forgive!
[gasps]
[KANDA]
There's no way.
[SKINN] Never forgive it.
Never forgive it!
He's still... alive?!
[SKINN]
Never forgive! Never forgive!
Never forgive! Never forgive it!
[KANDA grunts]
[KANDA] Dammit! I feel
like passing out again.
Hold on a little longer.
Bear the pain!
I'll never forgive.
No matter what!
[grunts]
[SKINN]
I'll never forgive you!
[SKINN shouts]
[KANDA shouts]
[SKINN screams]
[SKINN yells]
[KANDA grunts]
Mugen, activate!
Dammit...!
Why won't you die?!
[KANDA yells]
[SKINN] Did you forget?
We're immortal?
[KANDA]
It doesn't make sense!
He shouldn't be in any
condition to fight anymore!
I'll never forgive.
[grunts]
[SKINN] I'll never forgive.
I'll never forgive.
I'll never forgive...
[KANDA] Those words.
He just keeps repeating them.
How is he still able to stand?
The rage of Noah must be the
only thing keeping him alive.
That bastard! He's about
to fire a big one!
[KANDA grunts]
We're both in bad shape huh.
The Mugen is at its limit.
I can't afford another
direct hit from his attack.
[SKINN] I'll never forgive it!
I'll never forgive.
I'll never forgive!
The door's right behind me!
Mugen!
[KANDA]
Will you hold?
[KANDA grunts]
Nigen Swords!
I'll never forgive.
I'll never forgive it.
I'll never forgive...
you Exorcists!
[KANDA] He'll destroy the exit.
We have no choice, Mugen!
Sangen Style!
[KANDA] Take my life force
and grow strong. Mugen!
[KANDA grunts]
[grunting continues]
You can bear it. Mugen!
[SKINN shouts]
[KANDA shouts]
[KANDA] He's becoming
even more powerful!
But there's nothing left of him!
Where is this energy
coming from?
I'll never forgive.
[SKINN] I'll never forgive.
I'll never forgive Innocence!
Never!
[KANDA] So this is it.
The legendary rage of Noah.
I'll never forgive!
We are Noah. Immortal.
You are human. And will die!
[KANDA]
Death. I refuse it. Not until...
...I find the one
I'm searching for.
[KANDA gasps]
[SKINN sighs]
I did it.
I did it. I did it. I did it.
I did it. I destroyed
his Innocence.
I destroyed it.
[laughs]
I destroyed it! I broke the
Innocence into pieces!
[laughing continues]
[SKINN] Huh? That beam
of light nearly hit me.
But what the hell was it?
Not an attack.
No way. I destroyed
his Innocence!
[KANDA]
Mugen.
[SKINN gasps]
[KANDA]
Absorb.
Impossible! The light!
It's connecting the shattered
pieces of Innocence!
Joining them together!
[KANDA] This technique
is called Sangen Style.
It feeds off my life.
If I'm not dead. That means,
my sword isn't either.
[SKINN gasps]
[gasps]
[KANDA yells]
[KANDA]
It's done.
This battle is finished.
[grunts] You still
don't get it, Exorcist?
I already told you.
The Noah are immortal!
I'm not done!
Nothing's finished yet!
Far from it!
But why are you still alive?
Damn Exorcist!
And how were you able to
survive my attacks this long?
[KANDA]
I already told you.
[SKINN]
I see... You are... You're...
[SKINN groans]
This battle is concluded.
So shut up and die.
[KANDA grunts] I'm going
have to grovel with Komui
to put you back together.
[LENALEE]
Make sure you catch up with us!
[KANDA]
I wish... I could.
[KANDA grunts]
There's still... so much.
[KANDA] Heh. Regardless, they're
gonna give me hell over this.
[chuckles]
[rumbling]
What's that sound?
Huh?
[MIRANDA gasps]
Did anyone else feel that.
Someone's time has run out.
They've disappeared.
♪
[ALLEN] Believing Kanda
will soon join us,
we continue our efforts
to escape the Ark.
However, many obstacles
remain in our way.
Devices that could have
only been thought up
by a twisted mind. Or two.
On the next D. Gray-Man:
"The Twins' Traps."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
Hey you guys. Anyone seen Kanda?