[chuckles]
Not this guy!
[LENALEE gasps]
[BOTH yell]
[LENALEE]
Allen's hit!
Lavi!
He got both of them!
He's behind you!
What?
[ALLEN]
Clown Belt activate!
Getting confused?
I'm the one you're
supposed to be fighting.
That's why you're
here, isn't it?
For me. I'm the one
you wanna kill, right?
Getting careless or did
you forget? I'm still here!
[LAVI screams]
[ALLEN yells]
Is that it?
We may not get out
of here alive,
and this may be my last battle,
but I'll keep fighting
until my final breath!
That's the promise
I made with Mana!
[SKULL A]
I knew it.
You aren't one of the Skulls
our Master made, are you?
Interesting. So this must be the
egg you guys have been guarding.
That depends. Who're you?
[SKULL A yells]
[screaming]
[SKULL A laughs]
You're just wasting your time!
It's impossible for
you to get close!
It's a barrier spell.
You fool! Did you forget?
My Master, the illustrious
Millennium Earl,
has been a sorcerer
since the ancient times.
And only a sorcerer
can remove a spell.
Even Innocence is
powerless against it!
I see straight through
that disguise of yours.
Sadly, you're too late!
Because in mere moments,
this place will be
moved to the new Ark.
[SKULL]
A lecture on spells?
What good is that to a sorcerer?
Allen!
[yells]
[ALLEN yells]
Oh, no!
He's too powerful!
Oh, you think that's all
it takes to stop me?
You wish. This isn't over Tyki.
That's right. Bring it on.
[LAVI]
Okay. Let me keep him busy.
[gasps]
[yells]
[screams]
Allen!
Come down and fight!
[gasps]
Watch out!
[screams]
So I've caught myself
a filthy little scoundrel.
I was hoping you'd look at
least slightly better by now.
You're disgusting!
You haven't changed since
the day I took you in.
Stupid kid.
Wait a second.
That's the Anti-Akuma
weapon, Grave of Maria.
[ALLEN]
That means...
Uh. Hi again. Long time no see.
Listen, boy. Stop smiling at me.
Or I'll drop you.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[ALLEN screams]
Agh, that hurt.
No way.
Do you... know this guy?
It's him. General Cross.
Master.
[ALLEN]
Tim. You're here too?
[gasps]
[CROSS] So you're finally able
to activate it properly, eh?
[ALLEN]
Huh?
But other than that,
you look disgraceful.
Come here.
[ALLEN]
What?
Uh. O-Okay. Thanks for--
[ALLEN screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[CROSS] No apprentice of
mine looks like that!
And you. You might
as well join him.
I only allow clean, attractive
people to fight at my side,
and you two don't make the cut!
Wow, tell us how
you really feel.
[CROSS]
The Noah Clan, huh?
I wondered what could
possibly be so important
that you would be willing
to stay here and fight
aboard this crumbling ship.
I bet you've gone
insane, haven't you?
[MONSTER TYKI]
Exorcists.
The Noahs have control of you,
so this is for your own good.
[CROSS] On, Abata, Ura,
Masarakato. On, Gataru!
What's that?
He's gonna release
Grave of Maria.
[CROSS]
Activate.
[singing]
[CROSS]
Magdala Curtain!
Huh? It sounds like a hymn.
No, that's not quite it.
What?
Huh?
[CROSS] I thought it was wise
to send the brats away.
That's okay, isn't it?
[roars]
[LAVI]
So Tyki can't see us in here?
I don't think so.
That's what makes
Magdala Curtain so useful.
Master uses it to obstruct his
enemy's vision with sorcery.
That Maria thing will
only listen to his orders.
And that gun.
That's his Equipment-Type
Anti-Akuma weapon.
Time for Judgement.
[groaning]
Amen.
[ALLEN]
Grave of Maria and Judgement.
Other Exorcists carry a single
weapon, but my Master has two.
Did you say two weapons?
I didn't even know
that was possible.
[groaning]
[yells]
So changing the course of the
bullets is the most you can do?
Now I'm curious.
You see, my bullets don't stop
until they reach their target.
Wow. That's powerful.
She's right, Allen.
Your Master's amazing!
Uh-huh.
Maria.
[CROSS]
Over here.
Carte Garde.
[singing]
[screams]
I think we'd better
wrap this up.
No matter what we
threw at this guy,
we barely made a scratch.
And now look at him.
[CHOMESUKE] As you can see,
I may be an Akuma,
but I've been specially modified
by Cross Marian himself!
You should turn back around.
You'll only slow
the General down.
It kinda bums me out,
seein' how much more
advanced he is than us.
We got a long way to go.
Thank you.
Is this it?
It's about to collapse.
Hey!
That time, huh?
Well, I wouldn't
want to be late.
[gasps]
Huh. What do we have here?
[coughing]
That was no fun, Lero.
The Earl? Oh, boy, am I
happy to see you, Lero!
It's the Earl.
Wouldn't this be more fun if
we got rid of these awful brats?
No, Lavi!
[LAVI]
Extend!
[gasps]
[LAVI] Dammit! Tyki's attacks
must've worn it down.
I can't die now! No!
[ALLEN]
Lavi. Chaozii.
They're gone. It can't be.
[ALLEN screams]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Oopsie,
looks like I didn't
dispose of 'em all.
The ground!
[screams]
I'm okay.
Hey!
Oh, no. Is that blood?
Allen!
[ALLEN]
Don't worry.
I swear I'll save you!
But you can't let go!
Oh, Allen.
Allen!
[LENALEE screams]
You okay?
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Lavi... and Chaozii.
Where are my manners?
I haven't greeted ya yet.
Good evening, my friends.
[chuckles]
Well, now. You haven't
changed a bit.
Have you, you fat bastard?
[ALLEN]
Every second brings us closer
to the demise of Noah's Ark.
In hopes of stopping it,
my master, Cross, entrusts
me with a mission.
But what he asks of me is...
On the next D.Gray-Man:
"Shadow of the Player."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[ALLEN]
Hm?
Hey there.
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Well,
if it isn't Professor Cross.
It's been too long.
Honestly, where in the
world have you been?
Why, teaching my class,
of course, Principal.
Huh? Is that true?
But I thought...