Well, I'll admit, I was on pins
and needles there for awhile.
It was hard to know if
things would turn out well,
but thanks to Bookman,
Lenalee's recovered,
so I can breathe easy.
Ah, that's good to hear...
So, where are she
and the others?
They're en route to China
and I believe the journey's
been uneventful so far...
The last we were contacted
they were about
to cross into Tibet...
Of course I'll want you to
join them as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
Good, well, travel safe...
and be very careful.
Aww...
This is crap...
I want Lenalee's coffee.
She knows how to make it right!
Well she's not here so
that's obviously impossible...
In fact, Chief,
I'm pretty sure you
were the one that sent her away.
I know, but, need, my coffee...
This is important.
I need you to sign off on
these as soon as possible.
How could I forget
that no one makes coffee
like my angel Lenalee...?!
Oh man...
I hope he gets caffeine soon
'cause if it's gonna be
like this 'til she's back...
God help us all.
If it's true that Lenalee
and the others are about
to cross over into Tibet...
We should probably hurry
and meet up with them,
don't you think?
You're right...
The information we got
from the local
Finders checks out, too...
Now that we know my Master
was spotted in China
we can head there.
For the sake of the mission,
the sooner we join
our friends the better.
Well then, let's be off...
Tibet, here we come!
Wait a minute, before we go
I think we should find a guide.
Do we need one?
The best way for us to get
to Tibet from Nepal
is to probably cross
the Himalayas over there,
which could be rough.
I asked the people
at the hotel about it
and they all thought
it'd be too dangerous
for us to try to cross the
mountains by ourselves...
if we're gonna do it,
they said we should hire a
professional Sherpa to lead us.
But, why not?
Because it's not safe...
it's not a good time
to try to cross over...
I know the weather
looks clear right now
but there's a storm coming.
If you wanna make it
pass to the other side
alive you should wait
'til it passes through.
How long will that take?
Three days, a week,
maybe even ten days if it's bad.
Ten days...?!
But we can't make our
friends wait that long!
Plus, we know Master's
in China right now...
but he could easily
disappear again.
Uh, why are you
looking at me like that?
Because I found one.
I found a Sherpa to lead us!
Here...!
His name is Amyl
and he obligingly agreed
to take us over the
mountains into Tibet.
Oh, really?
But, the weather...
That man said we
shouldn't leave right now
'cause it's going to
get dangerous up there.
Well, it's always dangerous,
but I know a shortcut...
we should be able to pass the
ridge before it gets too bad.
It could be our best chance...!
I think we should
hurry and go now
or I'm afraid we'll miss our
rendezvous with the others.
Yeah... guess you're right.
Ah, there's plenty of food
in our packs for the journey.
So I think we should
all be set to head out...!
Come on men, to Tibet!
You might wanna slow down.
We need to be
careful on these paths.
Oh, don't worry about me,
Allen, I'll be fine--
See, what did I tell you,
you gotta watch out...!
Are you okay...?
Watch your step there...
Look how excited they
are to climb the mountain.
Too bad they'll never come down.
We'll finally be rid
of these Exorcists.
It's a brilliant plan...
Madame Lulu Bell.
We still have a long way to
travel before we reach China...
and I've been reminded
that we can't afford
to rest until we
locate General Cross.
He's a slippery one...
I really hope we meet up
with Allen and Krory soon...
that way we can all focus
on finding the General.
If he decides to take off
and go missing again...
it'd be too bad if we came
all this way for nothing.
Well, I know Komui
talked to them
and he said if
everything goes well
they should be
arriving here soon.
For all we know
they could have gotten
to town ahead of us...
We should hurry.
It's getting so cold!
When we were in the
foothills it felt like spring...
but it's getting nasty up here.
I hate to say it,
but I think that first man
we talked to was right.
We need to hurry.
I thought you said
this was a shortcut...
Didn't you say
if we followed you,
then we'd be able
to pass the ridge
before the weather
got rough like this!
Krory, please...!
We were the ones who
asked him to be our guide...
But it's--
Come on, let's keep going...
If the weather gets
much worse than this,
we are going to find
ourselves stuck up here.
He could be right...
how do we know this
is really a shortcut?
Oh, it's all my fault again...
I pressured Amyl into
bringing us up here...
If I hadn't asked him--
Krory, I've got you...!
Hang on, I'm gonna pull you up!
You... You saved me,
Allen, thank you!
We've got to keep
moving, alright...?
We have to cross the
ridge as fast as possible.
Did you hear me, Krory?
Come on, get up...
We'll make it through this...
What's the matter, you
didn't get injured, did you?
I think it happened
when I fell...
My foot hit the
rock pretty hard.
Please don't worry, I'm sure
it's nothing very serious...
In time, it'll heal
and be as good as new
so you should
probably go on ahead.
What are you talking about...?!
No way!
I'd never leave you here alone!
Oh, I'll be fine, Allen...
Think of the mission.
It's very important
that you get across
these mountains to find Lenalee
and the others...
They'll be terribly
worried if no one shows up.
I won't do it...!
Krory, I'm not going
to leave you behind!
Can't you see I don't want
to bring you any
more trouble...?!
You could have been
killed in that fall,
and all because
of my foolishness.
Forget about it, look at us.
We're both just fine.
Look, if you don't
think you can walk
on it then come here
and let me help you,
'cause there no way I'd ever
abandon a friend like that.
I'll be fine. I'm used
to being alone...
You forget that I used to spend
all my time alone in the castle.
At least until Eliade
appeared to me.
When I discovered
my love was an Akuma,
and destroyed her,
my life changed forever...
I became an Exorcist
and a member of the Black Order,
and gained many dear friends...
But I'm so naïve that
my thoughtlessness
has caused trouble
and put others in danger.
I just can't seem to
keep up with everyone else
and I don't want to
burden you any longer.
Don't be ridiculous. Let it go!
You've got to get up now...
We're leaving here together
and our friends
are waiting for us...
Lenallee, Lavi, and
Bookman will wanna see you.
But I'll just hold you back,
Allen, I know I will!
I'm gettin' mad... Stop it!
It won't work...
If we keep going
we'll be in big trouble.
Wait, so if we wanna make it,
we have to leave Krory here?!
No...
We all have to stay.
Wha-?
We should stop before
it gets any worse...
If we dig a hole now,
we can all wait there until
the storm passes over us...
A hole?
A tent would never
stay up in this wind...
Understand, we need to hurry...
Excuse me, it's mine.
No, it's mine...
I believe I saw you eating
an extra piece a minute ago.
You saw wrong. I didn't!
You did, too!
Well, fine...!
Crybaby...
Why, how dare you.
I thought you were
worried about me...!
And yet you'll let
me starve to death!
This doesn't mean
I don't care...
Actually...
I didn't consider
that we might have
to spend a few days
in here... and now...
This biscuit's the
only food we have left.
Crap, I'm so stupid...!
What are we gonna do now?!
Everything's ready on our end...
You can start any time...
Madame Lulu Bell.
Hey, about what
you said earlier...
You've never been a
burden to any of us, okay...?
Please believe me.
As a matter of fact,
everyone was so excited
when you became an
Exorcist and joined us...
...me, Lenalee, Lavi, Bookman,
and everyone else at the Order.
We've considered
you family ever since.
Three cheers for the Order's
newest member, Arystar Krory...!
Hip hip hooray!
Here's to Krory...
Uh... It's... good to be home!
Because we really are family,
we're going to cause
problems sometimes
and worry about each other.
But no matter what's happening
to us we'll always
stick together...
I mean, that's what a
family is for, isn't it...?
So don't talk about being a
burden or ask me to leave--
Hey, are you sleeping?!
Krory, wake up...!
Snap out of it,
if you fall asleep you're
gonna freeze to death...!
Come on...
Wake up, you have to
freakin' wake up now!
I can't... fall asleep yet...
I've got to... stay awake...
I wonder how long
I've been sleeping...
What's that... Is it...
How could Eliade
have gotten here?!
Wait!
Eliade... please
wait, don't go...!
Eliade... Eliade!
It is you!
Could it be an illusion...?
Perhaps I'm just dreaming now...
I'm wide awake...!
Then she really is here...
Eliade... thank you
for coming back to me...
I'm so happy to see you.
Forgive me my darling
but I'm so glad you
didn't forget me...
I've missed you
so... dear Eliade.
Please, won't
you speak to me...?
Say something and let
me hear your sweet voice.
Grandfather?!
What?
He's, an illusion...
Then Eliade must have been...
What's happening to me?
Mana?!
Mana!
Where did he go?!
It's impossible. I brought
salvation to his soul!
There's no way he could
come back to life...!
Someone's creating
an illusion for me...
Is it an Akuma?
Master!
You can't fool me...
I know you're an illusion!
Why would my
grandfather appear to me?
Lavi...! Oh, have
you come to rescue us?!
Thank heavens you're
here my friend...
I've started to go crazy
since I saw you last!
What... the soba noodle man...!
I hate Wasabi horseradish!
Lenalee?
I know it's not the real one...
but the body is solid
which means it must be...
Noah!
So that's it...!
Amyl is one of the Noah clan...!
And this was all just
a trap set to catch us.
Am I right?!
Wait!
Could that voice be...
Allen!
It is you!
It's a miracle, I was afraid
I was losing my mind...
You were right, I don't ever
want to be left alone out here!
Watch out, he's a fake!
There are two... Allens?
And he might also
be the same one
who showed up as Lenalee
to try to trick us...!
Get away from him!
Wha... Which one is--?!
Me...!
I'm the real Krory, Allen!
How can I know?
Don't listen to him...!
Can't you tell that I'm the
one and only Arystar Krory?!
Well, it doesn't really matter.
The real Krory has turned out
to be such a
headache to us all...
I might as well
wipe you both out!
You... You were really thinking
about me that way, Allen...
that I'm such a burden
to you and the others?
I knew it, I knew
I was a failure!
I told you before, that
I'm not worth saving...
Kill me, I have
no reason to live!
Uh...
I'd rather die than be
such a miserable wretch!
You're the fake!
Stop!
Damn... it disappeared.
The Akuma have
shown up, Krory...!
Hey, did you hear me,
get up and fight!
I just don't care anymore!
Yes, you do...!
Get up!
Akuma?!
Watch out!
Allen!
It's no big deal...
Just a little scratch.
Why even bother
trying to save my life...
when I'm really not
worth all the trouble.
Would stop it,
of course you are!
When we lost General Yeegar,
I made up my mind.
I'll fight... because if
I can't protect my family
I have no business
being an Exorcist.
Allen...
Watch this...!
I've got 'em now!
Huh?!
What do we do now?
We gotta move!
Yeah!
Allen!
What happened?
I think they were crushed
by the avalanche...!
It got the Akuma, too.
You finally took
them out, Madame!
Where am I?
Llhasa... in the
capitol of Tibet.
Lenalee...
But how did you guys find us?
Actually, you should thank Tim.
Timcanpy saved us?!
He sure did...
We thought you two
should've been here
by now so we decided
to go looking for ya...
it didn't take us
long to run into him
and then he led us
right back to you
and Krory laying there
passed out on top of the snow.
Thank you so much, Tim!
Hey, wait...
where's Krory?
Oh, I'm right here.
I'm so glad you're
finally awake.
It appears two comrades had
a hand in saving your life...
Soon after you were
buried in the avalanche,
Krory used the
last of his strength
to pull you out of the snow...
If he hadn't acted,
you'd both certainly be
frozen to death by now...
You owe him your
thanks, too... Allen.
Thank you...
You really came
through for us...
I'm very... very grateful.
Well...
I just thought that
family's supposed
to help each other out...
No thanks are needed.
I don't mean to get all
sentimental on you guys
but I gotta say I'm really glad
we're back together again...
Yeah, and now we
can finally get back
to our mission, right?!
Right...
I'm looking forward to it.
So they survived after all.
Those stupid Exorcists
must have the devil's luck!
It is unfortunate
they weren't killed...
however...
we did delay them.
My task was to
hinder their plans
to locate Cross by
complicating the journey...
and that was
successfully achieved.
Even if they do
manage to get to China,
they won't be able
to find him there.
He'll be gone by then.
In a town where the water supply
has mysteriously dried up,
we encounter a
remarkable girl...
Next time on
D. Gray-man: "The Crystal Girl."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul!