Oh my.
Beautiful.
What now...?
Yes, Kanda...?
I'm sorry sir, but we
don't have time to sketch.
You have to understand,
I may never visit this
place again in my life...
Now may be my only chance
to sketch this gorgeous
scenery before us.
I'll do it quickly
okay, I promise.
I bet I can get an even better
view from up on that bluff!
You'll get used to it...
It's just the way
the General is...
Yeah I know that.
Well, what do you know?
This spots taken.
Ah... A fellow artist.
Nice...
Your work is quite impressive...
Thanks, I really
appreciate that.
I noticed you like
to sketch buildings.
I'm studying architecture
at the university
over in Prague.
Interesting...
I take it that's
your profession...
How fun.
Nice meeting you.
I'm Alphonse Clouse.
And I am Froi Tiedoll.
These gentlemen here are
my travel companions...
Kanda and Marie.
It's a pleasure.
Sorry about him...
He's sort of the shy one...
It's nothing against you...
Ah okay.
So you said you came
here from Prague...?
If I were to guess I'd say
you came to these mountains
to see Jan's mansion, right?
Yes...!
You're familiar with it?
Well I'm at least
familiar with the rumors.
What is this...
mansion you speak of?
You see...
There used to be
an eccentric man
by the name of Jan Novark
who lived in a village
just ahead of here.
Jan owned a general store...
It was very well
known in the area
and packed with
customers every day.
Yet one day, out of the blue,
he decided to close it...
Taking the money he had
earned and investing it,
he began to build
a house for himself
with his own two hands.
His fellow villagers all assumed
he would get bored with
his new venture and quit...
but he did nothing
of the sort...
Day after day he continued
to build his house,
working his hands to the bone.
After a remarkable forty
years of construction,
he finally completed
the home of his dreams.
That is the story
of Jan's mansion...
I read this book as a child
and it had such a profound
effect it inspired me
to become an architect.
And now...
I'm so close to fulfilling
my childhood dream
of seeing his mansion
with my own eyes.
That's stupid.
Oh...?
I didn't know
you were listening.
It's hard not to...
I thought you couldn't be
bothered with such nonsense.
It doesn't interest me.
You just don't get it...!
It's a piece of art
that caused people
to take a fresh
look at architecture
from the perspective
of making a house fun.
Novak's ideas,
which weren't limited
to current thinking, surprised
the architects of his time...
His mansion is a
engineering triumph
that's inspired
writers and artists.
That mansion's a heritage
which should be
cherished by humanity.
The man is right... though...
I guess a cold fish like you,
wouldn't understand
the concept of cherishing.
What the hell are those?!
Move!
Noel Organon.
Marie...! Let's go!
Right... General!
Isn't that great...
There went our ride.
This place is deserted.
What the...
Why would everyone just up
and leave their meals like this?
This is an Akuma's doing.
Akuma?
You don't mean...
those monsters from earlier?!
Afriad so...
They didn't even
have a chance...
They're dead?
Found 'em...
East of here.
This way!
Wait up!
That's it...
Oh my lord...!
Look, it's Jan's mansion!
So you've finally
arrived, Exorcists.
We've been waiting for you...
In your absence; we decided
to kill all of the villagers!
Now come on inside so
we can have some fun!
How dare they mock
us by inviting us in...
Those bastards!
Kanda...!
Wait, it could be a trap.
Come on... Let's go...
We can not let them get away...
Boy oh boy...
I guess we have no other choice.
We'll go in for
a little while...
We simply can't
allow those Akuma
to run amok in such an
historic building as this.
B-But you...
Don't worry about us,
we'll be all right...
It would be best
if you left now.
Huh?
It's too dangerous...
Trust me this is no place
for a civilian like yourself.
Right...
Wait...
General...
Please protect the mansion!
I will...
It's a dead end.
Maybe this is it?
Take it easy there, Kanda.
Our enemies haven't even
shown themselves yet.
You heard what
Clouse said, didn't you?
This house was
designed with fun in mind.
Novak spent forty years
building this mansion
and he poured every
ounce of playfulness
he had into the structure.
Given that amount of time
the floor plan isn't simple...
as you can see.
Now this is convenient!
How refreshing!
Look here...
Now that is a nice touch...
This place is even more
fun than I had imagined.
General...
Could you please be more
careful with what you touch.
Hmm...
You say something?
The fun has begun.
Everything is going to plan.
But no matter how
many level one Akuma
we throw at those Exorcists...
It won't be enough to kill them.
But that's no surprise.
All they need to accomplish
is luring them into this room.
I see.
Only in this room do we
have an ideal battlefield
for our specific talents.
That it...? Then what do you
say we get a move on, huh?
Here... Let me try...
Your way of thinking is
inflexible... as always.
What... You assume
that when it comes to doors
you either push or pull.
Yet this one...
Is a pocket door...
You should try thinking outside
the box more often, Kanda.
Behind you...
Oh...
Welcome... Exorcists!
There you are, we've
been looking for you.
You seem quite relaxed,
General Tiedoll.
Oh... so you're
familiar with me?
Of course we are,
since our sole mission is
to take the Innocence
you're carrying.
I'm sorry to ruin your plans
but I don't see that
happening anytime soon.
Is that so...?
Then we will have no other
choice but to take it by force.
But before that, why don't
we set the stage a bit?
What the hell...
I take it by setting the stage,
you're referring to him?
No!
That fool came in on his own!
Have some patience.
The stage for our battle
will be finished soon.
I'm sorry... but
I couldn't resist coming in...
Then all of a sudden a hole
appeared in the floor below me.
Well, we'll just have to make
do since you're here now.
What's going on...
Behold!
The stage for our
momentous battle!
It will soon serve
as your graveyard!
I know this room...
It can morph... And
it contains
the most advanced devices
in the entire mansion!
This is the most interesting
house I've ever been in.
Well then, we agree
on one thing!
Perhaps we could
get along after all?
Don't push it...
I'm not known to
get along with Akuma.
Oh no...?
How unfortunate for you!
General...
Get him out of here...
You don't have to convince me.
It's all yours.
Innocence, activate!
What do you think?
Isn't my regenerative
body something else?!
Ahh...
This is going to be a problem.
Kanda! Move!
What a useless toy!
Marie!
See?
Isn't this fun?
It's like a giant puzzle,
but guess what, there's
even more to come!
I wonder how much longer
you'll be able to hold out?!
What's wrong...?
Have you already given up?
Found you!
Your face is your weak point.
This is getting hard!
Please stop it...
You're destroying the mansion!!!
This room is a work of art...!
What you're doing is a crime!
Please stop!
You're destroying my dream!
If you wanna walk
out of here alive,
shut your mouth and stay put!
Netherworld Creature Ichigen!
Wow.
Now there's nowhere
left for you to hide.
Well well...
That was quite
the show you put on.
But it appears you
went a little overboard.
No!
Amazing.
The mansion's control center!
Do us all a favor and fall
so the gears will
do the dirty work!
Geez...
To think you went so far as
to put our own
lives in danger...
You have a lot to learn.
Hey Clouse...
you put your own life at
risk to visit Jan's mansion...
Let it sear into your eyes.
Okay...
Maker of Eden... Activate!
What is he planning to do?
Art!
Wha... What the?!
No...!
It's collapsing!
I told you, didn't I?
You should be more flexible
in your way of thinking...
If you don't want them to
be able to hide anywhere,
you may have to
go to great lengths.
See?
They're right above you now.
It's time you finished them off.
It's a tragedy that
such a beautiful
and inspiring building
was lost today...
Words can't describe my sorrow.
But that doesn't make any sense,
he's the one who
just destroyed it...
You'll come to learn someday
that's just the way Master is.
In truth...
my father had fallen ill.
And due to that...
I couldn't continue my
studies in architecture...
I then decided to give up
my dream of becoming one.
I thought that once
I saw Jan's mansion
in person I could
put it all behind me...
But...
General Tiedoll.
I've made a decision!
I will... continue my
studies in architecture!
Ideas have started
popping into my head,
one after another...!
Like, what kind of
house would I build
if I were to use this
plot of land myself?
Now that Jan's mansion
is gone I have come
to realize my true calling...
It is to build a home
that surpasses its genius
while honoring Jan's original!
That's great.
Huh...
Makes me wonder
if Master destroyed the
mansion on purpose...
knowing it would have
this effect on Clouse.
I, for one, couldn't
possibly care less.
I go out for a while
to buy some snacks
and look what happens.
I wonder...
Do they enjoy sweets like me?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
While crossing the
mountainous terrain
to join up with the
rest of our group,
whom we were
separated from earlier,
we run straight into
a massive snowstorm.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"Illusions in the Snow."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.