[ROAD]
Allen!
Road? What...?
How I missed you!
Have you gone totally
insane, Mistress Road?
You can't kiss
an Exorcist! Lero!
[CELL] He's alive.
See? He's alive!
[TYKI]
Yes, yes. We can all see.
[ALL groan]
[TYKI] I got hungry while
we were waiting for you.
Care to join?
A chance to catch up before
we get down to business?
Afraid I'll have to
decline. You see...
We're kind of pressed
for time right now.
Speaking of which...
Would you care to know
how much time is left?
[ROAD] Look outside.
It's a wonderful view.
[TYKI] The only location
which still remains
is the tower we're standing in.
Everywhere else
has sadly collapsed
and disappeared for good.
[LENALEE]
It can't be!
[LENALEE, LAVI gasp]
Please stay awhile.
Come and join us.
Please, have a seat.
[ALL groan]
Unless you're frightened.
[LERO]
Le... Lero, Lero.
[ALLEN]
Road Kamelot.
[ROAD]
Go ahead and shoot.
[ROAD chuckles]
What a sweetheart
you are, Allen.
You really hate me, don't you?
Go ahead and shoot me.
But don't forget, that arm
of yours is also a weapon.
[ALLEN]
Tyki Mikk.
[TYKI] Poor boy.
Didn't you know?
Innocence isn't impervious.
Now then.
I believe that you and I are
overdue for a discussion.
Right, boy?
[TYKI] Oh, come on,
don't make that face.
It isn't becoming on you.
I promised you no
tricks, didn't I?
I'm not trying to trap you.
[ROAD giggles]
Yeah, don't be afraid, Allen!
[LERO]
What are you doing, Lero?
Stop hanging all
over him like that!
I set up the exit door!
It's all the way on the top
floor of this castle!
I hope it actually does
take us out of the Ark.
[ROAD giggles]
[LENALEE gasps]
[TYKI] The only location
which still remains
is the tower we're standing in.
[LENALEE]
Kanda.
Krory.
[LENALEE] We left
them behind. Are they...?
Let's try to be strong, okay?
Allen's trying, too.
[LENALEE] That's right.
I promised I'd try hard.
Get a hold of
yourself, Lenalee.
[LENALEE] This isn't
the time for crying.
Anita's death.
They had a hand in it.
[CHAOZII] Can she tell
what I'm thinking?
No. I'm just a regular human.
I can never defeat
one of the Noah clan.
[ALLEN] So tell me what this
is really about, Tyki Mikk.
Sorry, but I have no
reason to trust you.
You have no reason to act
all self-righteous, either.
I don't need to remind you
that you were the first Exorcist
to strip one of the Noah clan
down to his underwear.
You and I?
We're bound by destiny.
No, we're not.
Your friends lost their
shirts in that game too.
What makes you so special?
Now that is some
pretty big talk, boy.
You should respect your elders.
You want to talk about
my Innocence, right?
[TYKI chuckles]
To be quite honest, I was blown
away when I saw what happened.
I thought for certain I had
decimated that pesky thing.
Well, it's right here
in front of you.
So I guess that
you thought wrong.
Ooh. So Tycky's interested
in Innocence now? Who knew?
[TYKI] Perhaps a little bit.
Tell me, boy.
Teez devoured your heart and yet
here you stand, still alive.
I'm assuming that was
thanks to your left arm?
[BOTH gasp]
What'd he say?
Are you serious?
You mean your heart got eaten
and you didn't think it was
important to let us know?
[ALLEN] Uh, I just didn't
want you guys to worry.
Part of my Innocence
actually took the place
of my heart, so it's
not really a problem.
Allen, too?
[BOOKMAN]
Innocence making the choice
to save its Accommodator
is unprecedented!
[LAVI] That's crazy. When it
happened to Lenalee, it was
the first known case of a person
being saved by their Innocence.
[LAVI] But it's happened twice.
Lenalee and Allen.
At first we thought Lenalee's
Innocence might be the Heart,
but maybe we were
simplifying things too much.
There's supposed to
be only one Heart.
Now that we're
looking at two cases,
I'm thinking this
goes a lot deeper.
[ROAD] Are you
taking notes, Bookman?
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI]
Did she just...?
[ROAD]
Shh...
[LAVI gasps]
That's enough.
I'll have to ask you
to step away from
the boy, all right, Road?
No! I love him,
he's mine now!
You what now?
[LERO]
Mistress Road!
Don't be silly, Road.
You know very well that Noahs
and Exorcists can't be together.
[CELL]
Allen Walker!
[CELL coughs]
[TYKI]
Anyway. Lord Millennium
has the ending
all planned out.
I've played along
with it, half-seriously.
Evil should have a sense
of levity to it, no?
But thanks to you, boy,
I'm beginning to understand
what needs to be done.
[TYKI] In other words,
I should take
eliminating you
very seriously.
[ALLEN] Tyki Mikk. I have
something to say to you too.
If you do one more thing to
hurt any of my friends...
Then you'd better be
prepared for me to kill you.
[ALLEN]
Trust me, Lenalee.
I'll take care of
this guy for good!
You've got some nerve,
don't you?
I guess you're
not so bad after all.
Allen!
[ROAD] Well, how about that?
Turns out Tycky likes Allen too.
You best stay
out of it, Bookman.
Play with me instead, won't you?
It won't be long before
the ark disappears.
[ALLEN grunts]
Why don't we have
the last dance?
Well, well. Tell me, what
are you thinking right now?
Are you enjoying our quaint
little fight to the death?
Is it as much fun as when
you beat me at cards
the day we first met?
Lose the poker face and
tell it to me straight, boy.
Honestly, I'm sad. Every time
I see you, I'm reminded.
Of how you're not human,
and yet you are.
I wish this was
just a poker game.
If that's all it was, then
nobody would have to die.
[ROAD hums]
[LENALEE screams]
[CHAOZII yells]
[LENALEE]
What's happening?
Lenalee! Chaozii!
Well, it looks like
we're okay at least.
We're just locked in this box.
Yeah.
I'm keeping them locked away,
but I won't hurt them for now.
So let's play a game, okay?
Lavi...
What do you think
he's gonna do?
[LAVI] The oldest child
of the Noah clan.
Road, was it?
All right, fine, I'll play,
but you have to promise
to let them go if I win.
Eh. Sure, whatever.
Lavi!
[LAVI gasps]
[LENALEE]
Lavi!
Go, Teez.
Now, Crown Clown!
[ALLEN]
Clown Belt!
Lavi, no!
[ALLEN grunts]
[TYKI] I kinda feel
sorry for your friend.
You'd better hope
playing with Road
doesn't cause his mind to
completely disintegrate.
Oh, well. You should
worry about yourself first.
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN]
Right, I forgot.
You have the ability to pass
through anything you want.
[TYKI] Indeed. I'm not bound
by any object in the world.
In fact, I can even
walk through the air.
My powers allow me to
override any obstacle
or cross any barrier I please.
Well, technically. Innocence is
the one exception to that rule.
Ain't that a kick in the head?
It's not considered part
of this world, so...
[TYKI chuckles]
[ALLEN grunts]
[TYKI grunts]
[ALLEN yelps]
[LENALEE, CHAOZII sigh]
[ALLEN grunts]
Oh, Allen... Lavi...
Whoa. Where am I?
[ROAD] All you have to do
to win is find your way
out of this room.
Pretty easy game, right?
Time to start!
That's it, huh?
It's definitely not the
room I was in before.
She said she could
teleport, right?
I guess she must've taken me
to a different place somehow.
This is crazy.
It doesn't even look real.
[ROAD giggles]
What the hell are
you laughing at?
[ROAD laughs]
Nothing much. I was just
thinking about how confused
you must be right now,
trying to figure out
whether I teleported you
to a different reality.
[LAVI] Well, that's
what you did, isn't it?
So, how much longer are
you planning on sitting
inside the floor like a
creepy little chess piece?
Aren't we gonna fight?
[ROAD] Nah. That
wouldn't be fun at all.
[LAVI sighs]
Look behind you.
That's the person I want
you to fight instead.
[LAVI grunts]
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI]
Me?
That's a real cute trick,
but I'm still not buying it.
Fire Circle!
Devouring Flame!
[LAVI gasps]
[OTHER LAVI]
That won't work.
The only thing
here is your mind.
You don't have your
Innocence with you.
Which means that
you're powerless.
[LAVI gasps]
[ROAD]
Come on, Bookman.
[ROAD] Get real. If you
thought teleportation
was the only surprise
I had up my sleeve,
you've got another
thing coming.
[LAVI shudders]
[ROAD] The reason why I'm the
only Noah who can teleport
without using the Ark
is because I have
the unique ability to
connect reality with
my own little dream world.
Isn't that neat?
You and I are gonna have
so much fun together.
You might as well
get comfortable.
You're trapped in
Road Kamelot's dream
and I'm not letting
you out anytime soon!
[LAVI grunts]
[LENALEE]
Lavi!
What did she do to you?
Lavi! Speak to me!
What's happening, Lavi?
Come on, answer me! Lavi!
[ROAD laughs]
[LERO]
That's pretty dark, Lero!
Of all the Noah
family's abilities,
yours freaks me out the most!
First things first.
What part of that big old
Bookman brain of yours
will be the most fun for me
to poke at till it bleeds?
I hope your blood is a
nice pretty red color,
just like a candy apple!
[ROAD laughs]
[TYKI] Careful, boy.
Don't fall.
[ALLEN yelps]
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN gasps]
That's quite impressive.
It's like you're protected
by a full suit of armor.
You can call it a
clown if you prefer,
but from where I'm standing,
it looks more like a devil.
How fearsome.
This is getting
interesting.
I can't believe I get to destroy
your arm all over again.
[TYKI chuckles]
[ALLEN] Once again, I prepare
to battle Tyki Mikk.
Memories of our last fight
fill me with fear.
I do my best to hold my ground,
but in that moment,
an unexpected shock
passes through my left arm.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"Weak Humans."
Bring forth salvation
to this poor Akuma's soul!
[LERO] This'll be on the test,
Lero! Make sure you take...
Uh... Can I please see that?
Sure thing.
[LERO]
Huh? No, wait!
Are you crazy? Don't borrow
pencils from people who bring
their Golems to school, Lero!
Now give it back!
[ROAD]
Huh?
[ALL]
You're a Golem, too, Lero!