♪
[LENALEE] Krory!
He's hurt and needs us!
We have to go back
before it's too late!
We're not going to leave another
one of our friends behind!
Listen to me!
[gasps]
It'll be all right.
[KRORY screams]
[JASDEVI laughs]
[JASDEVI gasps]
[KRORY grunts, screams]
[JASDEVI]
He was one serious freak.
So long, Bloodsucker.
Your downfall was being
over confident enough
to think you could defeat
us in human form.
[JASDEVI grunts]
[JASDEVI] Ha! Looks like this
room has just about had it.
[JASDEVI] Seriously! How much
longer are we going to have
to wait for Cross to show up?
I swear. He's almost as
annoying as that vampire.
[footsteps]
[ELIADE] What do
you think you're doing
in a place like this, Arystar?
[KRORY] Who are you?
[ELIADE sighs]
I swear.
You really can't do
anything right, can you?
[KRORY]
That voice. No. It can't be.
[ELIADE] All this time I
thought you became an Exorcist
to atone for killing me,
your sweet Eliade.
And yet. I find you sacrificed
yourself for somebody else.
Fighting to protect those kids.
One thing never changes
about you, Arystar.
You don't see things through.
[KRORY chuckles]
[ELIADE]
What are you laughing about?
[KRORY] Are you here
to welcome my soul?
[ELIADE gasps]
[ELIADE]
Stop being so ridiculous.
What?
You think I've come to escort
you to the gates of Heaven?
[ELIADE] You might actually make
it up there, but I never will.
I'm merely an ego trapped in the
body of an evolved Akuma.
Nothing more.
[ELIADE]
I don't have a soul.
Not like you. If you
wanna go, go alone.
[KRORY]
Eliade.
[ELIADE] You want to get back to
those kids. Don't you, Arystar?
[ELIADE]
It's understandable.
After all, they were the first
humans to befriend you.
[ALLEN]
Krory!
Are you ready to head with
us to the Black Order?
Oh, the name's Allen.
And you can call me Lavi.
I'm an apprentice to this geezer
named Bookman who I'm sure
you'll meet soon enough.
[ALLEN]
All right. Let's go.
And don't worry about
what the villagers say.
Starting from this
moment forward,
you're considered one
of us, an Exorcist.
So, Krory. How does that sound?
[gasps]
[LENALEE]
I'm Lenalee.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
What're you waiting for?
When a woman
offers you her hand,
you should be polite
and shake it.
A woman?
She's just a young girl!
What? Why aren't you
frightened of me, little girl?
[LENALEE]
Hm?
I mean. Don't I look
like a vampire?
[giggles]
[gasps]
Bookman's face is a lot
scarier than yours!
[whimpers]
[ALLEN, LAVI chuckle]
[ELIADE]
You can't go to heaven yet,
or you'll be all alone again.
You used to only
think about yourself.
[ELIADE] This is the
first time you've wanted
to protect someone else.
You're not ready.
[gasps]
[ELIADE]
You should return to those kids.
[KRORY]
Eliade.
I still love you. Truly I do.
Even if this is a hallucination.
Thank you, my love
[ELIADE]
Now, accompany them.
To the depths of
hell if need be!
You ready, Krory? Let's go.
[KRORY]
Yes. It's time to go.
[JASDEVI]
Now to deal with Allen Walker.
He'd better not be dead yet.
Imagine if Tyki kills him
before we get to him.
[JASDEVI] He still has to
answer for his Master's debt.
[metalic groan]
[JASDEVI gasps]
[gasps]
[JASDEVI grunts]
Let go!
[gasps, grunts]
That really hurt!
Who do you think you--?
[gasps]
[KRORY growls]
Hey now. What the
hell is going on?
[KRORY] Protect them.
I will protect them.
You will not bring
harm to my friends.
We know that voice!
You're the vampire!
[KRORY growls]
[JASDEVI gasps]
[JASDEVI] This smell.
It reeks of blood!
His whole body is covered in it.
How'd he get out of
the iron maiden?
[JASDEVI] No way!
His body is still in there!
[JASDEVI] That means.
This must be his Innocence!
When he couldn't
move his body anymore,
he abandoned it. And took
a form that was solely
comprised of blood
possessed by his Innocence!
Chomesuke's blood. I want it!
[JASDEVI screams]
Bastard vampire! Die!
[KRORY grunts]
I certainly got it
all back and more.
[KRORY screams]
[JASDEVI grunts]
[screaming continues]
[KRORY screams]
[JASDEVI] Damn freak!
[screaming continues]
The real devil is
your Innocence.
That's why. It has to be killed!
Die! You demon!
[JASDEVI gasps]
[KRORY]
I will protect my friends!
[JASDEVI grunts]
[JASDEVI] What is this?
A nightmare?
[JASDEVI, KRORY grunting]
Dammit! We've had enough!
Go back to hell!
That's where you belong!
Monsters like you shouldn't
be allowed in this world!
Now that you mention, I suppose
we do have something in common.
Bastard! I'm nothing like you!
[JASDEVI screams]
[JASDEVI grunting]
[JASDEVI grunts]
The spot he hit us. Feels like
something broke through
our skin and entered our body.
[gasps]
What. What did you do?
[JASDEVI screams]
It can't be.
We've been infected.
[JASDEVI gasps]
Look what you've done to us!
[JASDEVI]
Filthy monster!
I will protect them!
[KRORY] My friends make
me stronger than you!
[JASDEVI yells]
[KRORY growls]
[MIRANDA gasps]
Oh, no!
[MIRANDA]
Not again!
[JASDEVI grunts]
What we need...
...is a rest.
[coughs]
Just a little break.
[DEVIT]
Jasdero...
[JASDERO]
...and Devit.
[gasps] It feels like my senses
are beginning to return.
[KRORY] My body.
So full of pain all over.
It's so cold. I can barely
keep my eyes open.
[KRORY] But, there's one thing
that brings me comfort.
I know Allen and the others were
able to keeping moving forward.
[KRORY] I'll join them after
I've rested just a little while.
[LENALEE grunts]
[ALLEN] I promised. I said
we're all going home together.
That includes
Kanda and Krory.
We're making it out alive.
I swear I'll do everything I can
to make sure that happens.
[LENALEE]
Allen.
Since you've returned to us,
you've somehow grown stronger.
Unfortunately, I didn't
realize how weak and afraid
I had become.
Ever since I lost
control of my Innocence,
I've grown worried, and scared.
[LENALEE]
Just a while ago,
the most terrible vision
entered my head.
A ghastly future.
I couldn't stop.
[LENALEE] No! Don't think
about such things!
[LENALEE] I can't lose the
will to fight. Not now!
If I do. I'll be
dragged into darkness.
[LENALEE] I've got to believe.
Trust more. Be stronger.
I'll try harder.
[ALLEN gasps]
[LENALEE]
Hm? Did I say that aloud?
I knew you were tired.
You shoulda told me.
No! I just got lost in thought.
Really, I was thinking about
how much I need to train
when we get back home.
Training? That's the
first thing you're doing
when you get back
to the Order?
When I get back,
I'm gonna sleep!
And not just a nap!
I'm talking hibernation!
[LENALEE] There's nothing
wrong with sleep!
I just figured training's
important too!
[LAVI] You can't be
serious all the time.
Otherwise you'll never
find a boyfriend.
Do you even have a boyfriend?
--[LENALEE growls]
--[LAVI grunts]
[LENALEE] That's none
of your business, Lavi!
[ALLEN]
Talk about rude!
[LAVI]
Ow. That hurt!
Hey, I apologize! I was curious.
Huh?
[LAVI] Uh, so what're
you gonna do, Allen?
About?
[LAVI] Afterwards.
When we all get home.
I've given it thought,
and the answer... is eating!
Jerry is incapable of cooking
a meal I won't devour!
[LAVI sighs]
Of course.
[LENALEE]
It's always food.
[CHAOZII chuckles]
I didn't mean to laugh.
But the way you guys were
interacting just now.
It's like you're
ordinary people.
[CHAOZII] I guess I
thought Apostles of God
would somehow be different.
More stoic.
I didn't think you'd laugh,
tell jokes,
Or that you'd sometimes
be afraid. You know?
I thought you'd be unfeeling.
[chuckles nervously]
[CHAOZII gasps]
Chaozii, we're ordinary people.
Of course there are
times we feel scared.
Listen. When that happens,
think of something fun
and you'll stop worrying.
It'll cheer you up. Trust me.
[CHAOZII gasps]
[LERO]
Are you serious?
You think this the time
to relax? You're doomed
and no amount of daydreaming
is going to change that, Lero!
You're wrong about that, Lero.
[LERO]
Heh?
For me. I think about
seeing our friends.
And all of us going home.
Surprising Komui.
No matter how
hopeless things seem.
Even if it looks like
we're doomed for sure.
I'll never stop
fighting or give up.
[LERO]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[LERO]
Lero.
[LAVI] Allen's determination.
It's shining, radiating.
I wonder. What kind of
weight are you carrying
on your shoulders underneath
that clown Innocence?
[LAVI] You're such an intense
light. Please, don't burn out.
[ROAD]
Allen!
Road? What?
How I missed you!
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALL yelp]
[ROAD sighs]
[LERO] Have you gone totally
insane, Mistress Road?
You can't kiss
an Exorcist, Lero!
Oh! Lero!
[LAVI] Allen! Get a
hold of yourself!
Did she put you in a coma
with her poisoned lips? Allen!
[TYKI]
What were you thinking, Road?
Don't tell me you actually
like the boy that much.
[CELL]
Allen Walker!
[giggles] You're not
jealous are you, Tycky?
[CELL]
He's alive. See? He's alive!
[TYKI]
Yes, yes, we can all see.
[ALL]
Uh...
[TYKI] I got hungry while
we were waiting for you.
Care to join?
[CELL]
He's alive.
A chance to catch up before
we get down to business.
Afraid I'll have to decline.
You see, we're kind of
pressed for time right now.
Speaking of which.
Would you care to know
how much time is left?
[gasps]
[ROAD] Look outside.
It's a wonderful view.
The town. Where'd it go?
[ALLEN gasps]
[TYKI] The only location
which still remains
is the tower we're standing in.
Everywhere else has sadly
collapsed and
disappeared for good.
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
It can't be!
[LENALEE, LAVI gasp]
Please stay awhile.
[TYKI] Come and join us.
Please, have a seat.
[ALL grunt]
Unless you're frightened.
[LENALEE gasps]
[LAVI grunts]
♪
[ALLEN] We've arrived at the
tower only to find Road Kamelot
and Tyki Mikk waiting for us.
As the time limit approaches
and the Ark collapses,
the fated battle begins.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"Dark-Colored Rhapsody."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[KRORY grunts]
Everyone must have gone home.
[KRORY]
Guess I'll sleep some more.
[ELIADE]
You such a dummy.