A fragment of Innocence was
discovered in southern Italy...
But we got word that an Akuma
is already en route to grab it.
You two will head
there immediately.
Destroy the enemy and secure
the Innocence at all costs.
According to the dossier
we're heading to...
the ancient city of Mater...
I think I remember reading
about this place once.
It's been in ruins for decades.
Our target sounds interesting.
The Ghost of Mater...
I'm confused.
Innocence has altered
its own biology.
Of course it doesn't
happen overnight...
Most estimates
place the timeline
between Noah's
Flood and the present.
The one thing we
still can't figure out
is why Innocence is causing
the strange phenomena.
What the... There's two of me.
I copied you...
It was easy...
I even duplicated your power.
Look out, the Akuma
is right beside you!
Forgive me...
but I had to...
You are the doll...
The Ghost of Mater.
Hey... Hold on!
Stop this, tell me why
you're attacking us...
Come on, I'm no good fighting
against a cute girl like you.
Very soon Guzol will be dead...
Please don't take me
from him until he's gone.
I'll let you have my heart
just don't separate us!
Did you know that when there
were still people in Mater;
it used to be called
"the land forsaken by God"?
Yes...
I've heard of that.
Trying to escape the harsh
weather and the blazing sun...
the citizens began
to dig underground...
and they built living
spaces down in the earth.
They kept digging and
digging for years on end
until finally... one day...
they found something.
They were suffering
and in great despair...
and their city was slowly
dying around them.
They created a doll that
would bring them comfort,
that would help them to
forget those hard times...
even if just for a minute.
A doll... that would
sing and dance.
Even after the city went to
ruin hundreds of years later...
and there was no one
left to hear the song...
this doll kept on singing...
alone in the world.
Then one day...
a small child arrived in
the now abandoned town...
He had no family...
and had simply wandered around
until he discovered Mater.
Little boy... would you
like to hear a song?
Little boy...
would you like to hear a song?
It had been five hundred years
since Mater had
ceased to exist...
and it wasn't the first time
a human had
stumbled into the city.
I met five adults over
the years before he came...
but when I asked each of them
if they wanted to hear a song...
they all attacked me...
I thought the boy would
do the same thing.
I was just going to kill him
if he didn't accept me...
as I did to all of the
others before him.
Little boy...
would you like to hear a song?
I'm a doll created by humans...
and doing their bidding...
is the reason for my existence.
Please... let me sing for you!
Miss Ghost?
You would really sing
a song for me...?
No one has ever done
anything like that.
Miss... my name is Guzol...!
Please sing for me, oh please!
Just look...
Your hair is so
pretty now, Lala!
Lala?
Can I please call
you that, Miss Ghost?
Several decades have
passed since then...
and Guzol has stayed
with me all this time.
Oh, Guzol, are you alright?
Lala... stay by my side...
until the end...
and let me stop you...
with my own hands...
when I die.
Yes... Guzol...
I belong to you
and so does my fate.
He will soon be unable to move.
I can barely feel his heartbeat
as it grows weaker...
So please give us
a little longer...
Let me be here with him
until he passes on.
During the past
five hundred years...
since the city of
Mater became ruin...
Guzol has been the only
one who accepted me.
I promise I will gladly
hand my heart over
to you when he is gone...
if you will let me stay with him
as his doll until the end.
Please, I beg of you!
We can't.
You're asking us to wait around
until that old man dies...?
We don't have time for that--
we don't know when the
Akuma will discover us here.
Kanda!
What did we come here for?!
Get over there and take
that doll's heart short stack!
I can't.
I'm sorry...
but I don't want to take it.
Then take this--
that coat wasn't made to
be used as a damn pillow...!
It was to be worn
by an Exorcist!
Sacrifice is what leads
to salvation... hear me?
No, please don't
take it from me yet!
Please... not just yet...
Stop.
Let me be the one.
Step away from them and let me
become the sacrifice instead...
As far as I can see they just
want to choose the way
their lives end, nothing more.
And until that
happens I won't take
the Innocence from this doll...
If I destroy the
Akuma there should be
no problem honoring
their request...
How can you stand there
and be so cold blooded
towards these people?
Is this really worth--
Please--this won't
solve anything!
Your naïve outlook
is ridiculous...!
You'd compromise
yourself for others just
because you feel
sorry for them?!
Where is your pride?
Don't you cherish anything?!
Kanda you're wrong...
I don't feel sorry for them...
It's my pride that...
helps me stand up against
your anger right now.
I feel sorrow for them
because their bond will
soon be destroyed...
I mean, doesn't...
that mean anything to you...?
You know they don't
have much longer.
You'll still get the Innocence.
All they're asking for is time!
So I'll gladly offer
myself in their place
if you'll just let them be!
Guzol...
It's him.
I got the Innocence!
It's mine!!
La... la...
Lala...
My my...
It's more beautiful
than I dreamed!
Give it back...
Give the Innocence back...
Give it back!
Give the innocence back...
Right now.
You hear me?
His Anti-Akuma weapon
is transforming!
Yes, he's going
to rebuild it...!
Parasite Type
Exorcists can alter
their weapons with emotions.
Even the Innocence appears to
be reacting to his feelings...!
Amazing...
His emotions are
incredibly powerful...
His weapon is a manifestation
of his hatred towards the Akuma.
Idiot...!
The weapon hasn't completed
it's formation yet!
What is that?!
It's a gun!
You can't hurt me with that
thing if I'm sand, can you?!
Comfy, right...?!
This is it...! While you die,
I keep the innocence!!
Mind if I help you
with dying??!
Oh no! Master Walker!
He's fine, Toma.
I'm still sensing
the kid's hatred.
He started shooting
from the inside!
I feel the Innocence
inside me doing all this...
firing my nerves and
directing my brain...
My brain controls my body
and teaches me a new
way to use my Weapon!
It changed... again!
Oh no...!
My skin...
The sand...
was...
Sand...
Sand!!
You're not going anywhere.
That much I promise you.
Don't forget I still
have your right arm!
Lala...
stay by my side...
until the end...
and let me stop you...
with my own hands...
when I die.
He loved her...
I won't let you get
away with this...
I won't!
Dammit...
I don't understand...
How can he be beating me...
We're using... the same arm?!
The kid has a limit...
It's changed its form,
but his anti-Akuma weapon
only has so much energy...
Only exorcists that
are fully synchronized
with their Innocence
can use their weapon
to its most
powerful potential...
Judging from what I've
seen--the boy isn't there yet...
Ow... damn...
A rebound...?!
Why isn't my body able
to handle this new weapon?
I win!
You're alive?!
Kanda!
Shut up, you wimp!
You're going to quit now
that you're a little tired...!
If you give up, you'll
never be a true exorcist...
You said you wanted to
protect them... right...?!
Right?!
That's why I hate you--you're
so damn lazy, short stack...
destroy this Akuma
and save these people...
or just give up and die.
Okay, in that case...
if you're gonna
hate me anyway...
I never actually told
you I would give up.
I just needed to catch
my breath, that's all.
Everything about
you is annoying.
Give me one more shot...
please...
Innocence...
activate!
Underworld Creatures...
First Illusion!
Be vanquished!
Impossible...!
Damn you to hell!
One more time...
I wanna hear Lala...
Do you want a song?
Mister Human?
Mi-ster hu-man...
I am a doll.
I'll sing a song...
Mi-ster hu-man.
Lala...
I love you.
Are you going to sleep now?
Then I will sing...
a peaceful lullaby
for the nice human.
You sleeping...?
You'd better keep a
close eye on that doll.
Yeah... Are you okay?
I heal quicker than most people.
Really...?
You looked pretty bad.
Shut up.
I was able to make contact
with the Order a while ago
and Komui has
given us instructions...
I'm headed straight to the
next assignment from here...
It's your job to bring the
Innocence to Headquarters.
I got it.
If it's too hard,
just go stop her...
It's not even
really Lala anymore.
You're right...
but it's the promise they had...
Guzol has to be the one
who finally stops her song.
You're too soft, you know that?
An exorcist is
simply a destroyer...
We'll never be anyone's savior.
I don't think I agree...
We can be both.
On the third night...
after Guzol died...
Lala stopped.
Thank you...
for letting me sing
until I broke down.
You helped me keep my promise--
Hey... what's wrong with you?
Kanda...
We're not just destroyers...
At the same time...
we can be saviors.
In the town, a voice shouts
that an Akuma
has been spotted...
The boy wanted to go after
it more than anything.
It's dangerous!
Stay away from the
Milennium Earl...!
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"That Which Calls
forth Disaster."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!