♪
[SKINN grunts]
[KANDA]
It's done.
This battle is finished.
[SKINN grunts] You still
don't get it, Exorcist?
I already told you.
The Noah are immortal!
[SKINN] I'm not done!
Nothing's finished yet!
Far from it!
[SKINN groans]
This battle is concluded.
So shut up and die.
[KANDA] Heh. Regardless, they're
gonna give me hell over this.
[chuckles]
[ROAD]
Rest in peace, dear Skinn.
So the sugar freak lost.
[ROAD]
Yes and no.
Someone stayed behind while
Allen and the rest went
on ahead. But it appears he
never made it through the door.
[TYKI] They must have
killed each other.
[ROAD]
Tyki! Are those tears I see?
You don't have to touch me.
They just started
flowing on their own.
[ROAD giggles]
[TYKI]
What's going on?
It's like the Noah
inside of me is crying.
[chuckles]
I bet that's the reason.
And we're probably not
the only ones either.
[DEVIT grunts]
Curious.
Road, you wouldn't
happen to have any tissues?
I didn't realize you cried
tears as black as your heart.
Stupid Tyki!
This is an emergency!
Our makeup is running!
[BOTH grunt]
Use those.
Don't we have any
cleaning rags around?
Do you want to die?
[BOTH grunt]
[chicken clucks]
We should hold a party
for Skinn. A proper send off.
[footsteps]
[LENALEE gasps]
[gasps] Hey Lenalee.
Is something following us?
It's just. Kanda said he'd
catch up, but he hasn't shown.
[LERO] I bet he was
taken out by Skinn, Lero!
[gasps]
I'm sure he'll rejoin
us any minute.
I volunteer to go
back and check on him.
Make sure nothing's wrong.
[CHAOZII grunts]
Kanda doesn't want us to worry.
[LERO] You Exorcists don't
really think Skinn was defeated!
When are you gonna learn?
The members of the Noah
Clan are immortal, Lero!
Immortal or just
undefeated so far?
[CHAOZII grunts]
You know, there's a
big difference between
being invincible and not having
faced a greater opponent.
[LERO] Huh? Yeah? Well, even if
your friend is alive,
once the information is
completely downloaded to the
new Ark, the room he's in
will disappear forever, Lero!
We're going to find the
exit and escape the Ark
before that happens.
But we have to keep
moving forward.
Trust that Kanda will keep his
promise and eventually catch up.
He did promise. Allen's right!
Then we keep pressing onward.
Agreed!
I don't know what happened,
but you've certainly
grown stronger.
[chuckles] And believe me,
when Kanda gets back,
I'm not letting him
call me short stack.
Stronger, but still annoyed
by "short stack"?
Being called short stack
isn't even that
tremendous of an insult.
[LENALEE]
Hm. Let's move, you two.
To Skinn. Farewell.
See ya, big guy.
[TYKI sighs]
[JASDERO] Here come
the waterworks again.
Why can't we control them?
[ROAD sighs]
Remember, it was
Skinn who carried
the memory of the Noah's anger.
Jasdevi carries the "bond".
Tyki carries the "pleasure"
Lulu Bell has the "lust".
And lastly, I hold the "dream".
But unlike the
rest of our traits,
"anger" is the most intense and
powerful of Noah's memories.
[DEVIT]
It's true.
Out of all of us, ol' baldy
was always the moody one.
[JASDERO] Hard to figure out!
Right to the end!
[ROAD] Even though we're
all children of Noah,
and the sight of an Exorcist
never fails to fills us
with the desire to kill,
Skinn was different.
We struggle to
control our memories,
but the one who holds wrath
is a puppet to their emotions.
[DEVIT] So fighting was the
only way he could relate to us.
[JASDERO]
The most tragic of the Noah!
We'll never forget him!
[TYKI] By the way,
didn't the Millennium Earl
order you to find Cross?
So where is he?
[DEVIT, JASDERO]
Huh?
Whoa. Can you
believe this guy?
Asking us at a time like this?
Do people do that?
[TYKI] Just as I thought.
You failed again.
Shut up! So what if he escaped?
What are you gonna do about it?
Yeah! And maybe we're terrified
to go tell the Millennium Earl?
So what about it?
[clucks]
I just have difficulty believing
Cross is that elusive.
Maybe I should
capture him for you.
[BOTH]
We already told you, he's ours!
We were close this time
but when we got there,
all we found were
chickens! Chickens!
Ah! So that explains why
you're carrying a rooster!
[DEVIT] That bastard Cross!
He's mocking us!
Does he think he can make
fools out of Jasdevi!
He made fools out
of us using fowls!
[DEVIT, JASDERO grumble]
And what do we have here?
Looks like bills.
Those are the bills
Cross saddled us with
after skipping out of town.
[ROAD]
Huh?
[DEVIT shouts]
Idiot! Don't tell her!
So not only did you
let him escape,
you got stuck paying for
his booze and lodging?
[ROAD giggles]
[JASDERO grunts]
I swear. Cross is a dead man!
Huh? What's this
signature down here?
Oh yeah. Him. It must
be his apprentice.
He's more unlucky than us. Ha!
[ROAD giggles]
Listen up, Jasdevi.
I've got some news for you
I think you're going to like.
[LAVI] How far do you
suppose this hallway goes?
Feels like we've been searching
for the second door forever.
[CHAOZII]
Yeah.
[JASDERO] So that's
Cross's apprentice, huh?
[JASDERO chuckles]
Then we better go deliver
these bills to him.
Care to explain why you
let them inside the Ark?
Well I believe dreams
are the most enjoyable
when you're dreaming them.
Go on.
But when a dream
becomes reality,
suddenly the
illusion is over.
So even though the thought
of destroying Allen Walker
does bring a smile to your face,
the idea of the twins tormenting
him first is more
rewarding to you?
You got it.
Here.
That's some twisted
mind you've got.
[ROAD] See? The moment
before the attack.
The build up is always
the most exciting part!
[gasps]
[CHAOZII]
What's going on?
Liquor bottles?
But who put them in the hallway?
[JASDERO]
We did!
And you should probably know,
there's a bomb planted in one!
But so many to choose from!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
If you don't find and defuse
it soon, you'll all be spirits!
[JASDERO laughs]
Who would think of
a trap like this?
They could be lying.
--[ticking]
--[all gasp]
[LAVI]
I've got this side!
[KRORY grunts]
Which one is it?
[LERO]
Move faster, Lero!
[ALL grunt]
[ALLEN] I know these bottles.
I recognize all these brands.
[LENALEE]
Huh?
It's coming back.
The memory of going out
to buy booze for my master.
General Cross did that?
And I had to put
them all on a tab!
[ALL gasp]
It got to a point where
no one would sell to me.
"My! You're running
up a large bill!."
"Go support your habit
some other place!"
But it wouldn't matter.
If I showed up empty-handed,
I'd still get scolded.
"Go find me some! And don't
come back till you do!"
So I pleaded and
begged around town.
Until someone took pity
and sold me a bottle!
Uh, Allen.
I don't really think this is
the time to get nostalgic.
And the most expensive alcohol
among them all was...
[ALLEN]
This one! The prized drink!
[ticking]
[LENALEE gasps]
The bomb! It's inside!
[ALLEN grunts, gasps]
Why are you waiting? Defuse it!
Hurry up!
How do we defuse it?
And we've only got
eight seconds!
Just get rid of it
before it explodes, Lero!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[yelps]
Allen, toss it this way.
You got it!
[LAVI shouts]
[BOTH gasp]
[DEVIT]
Stay away!
[BOTH shout]
[CHAOZII]
Talk about a close call.
Well done. That was
quick thinking.
Yeah, it was a piece of cake.
Why are bottles of my master's
favorite alcohol here?
Please, don't tell
me he's somewhere
inside the Ark with us.
That might be the case. If so,
it's good news. Right, Allen?
[ALLEN]
What?
This master of yours would
never try to bomb his pupil,
would he?
He would never stoop
to such a level!
Then again, I could be wrong.
Regardless, we should
keep moving forward.
[grunts] The thought of my
master waiting for us somewhere
in the Ark is troublesome.
I want to find him, but at
the same time I don't.
[LERO]
Uh...
Why do I get the feeling
I know who's behind this?
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[CHAOZII shouts]
[KRORY] So now we're
going to be skewered?
[ALLEN]
Playing cards?
[DEVIT] You have three seconds
to make the exact poker hands
I tell you! And no mistakes!
[JASDERO] Or else we're going
to let this spiked ceiling
cut ya to pieces!
[JASDERO chuckles]
First up, three of a kind!
Done!
For your next hand.
Let's see a full house!
Done!
[JASDERO]
Correct!
Wow, he's fast.
I expected nothing less.
And, for your last hand,
a royal flush!
Game.
[DEVIT]
Three for three!
You're incredible, Allen!
Oh, I don't know if
I'd go that far.
[DEVIT] You won, but we're gonna
drop the ceiling anyway! Ha,ha!
[KRORY]
Wait, that's not fair!
[CHAOZII]
What are we gonna do?
[LAVI]
Cut us a path!
[ALLEN grunts]
[LAVI grunts]
[KRORY]
Phew!
Come on. Let's go.
[LAVI gasps]
Only two people are capable
of such childish pranks. Lero.
[DEVIT] Heh. Don't think we're
finished with you yet.
[DEVIT chuckles]
First alcohol, then cards.
Both things remind you of
General Cross, don't they?
Uh, yeah.
[gasps]
And now a giant roulette table.
What do you say?
How about we ignore this
one and just keep moving?
I completely agree.
Hold on a sec!
If you don't play along,
it's rigged to explode!
[JASDERO] Your lives are the
chips to gamble with!
Do you pick black? Or red?
Who's behind these
morbid games?
[DEVIT] And, it'll explode
if you don't win!
[CHAOZII gasps]
[LERO]
Don't drag Lero into this!
[ALLEN chuckles] Well, life is
a gamble after all!
Wait. What're you saying?
What kind of reckless life have
you been living up until now?
No choice. Looks like we're
going to have to place a bet.
Right! We'll leave it
in your hands, Allen.
Since it appears you have more
experience than the rest of us.
We're counting on you to win!
I'll do my best.
[exhales]
Everyone, go to red!
[DEVIT] No more bets!
Start up the roulette!
[ALL grunt]
[ALLEN chuckles]
[ALLEN]
Hey.
[ALL gasp]
[JASDERO yelps]
You're nothing but a cheat!
I don't suppose
you have any proof?
I saw you hit the
table with your leg!
You hit it with your leg!
Really? I don't remember.
He's quite brazen
with his cheating.
Or you could say experienced,
depending on how you look at it.
[BOTH]
You play dirty!
You're the one's hiding
up in the ceiling.
If you and I are so different,
why don't you prove it
and show yourselves?
[DEVIT] Fine then! We'll come
down and reveal ourselves.
Just walk straight ahead.
You'll find us waiting for
you at the end of the hall.
[JASDERO]
That is if you ever make it!
[JASDERO laughs]
[rumbling]
[ALLEN gasps]
Is there something wrong, Allen?
I thought I heard a
noise coming from
further down the corridor.
Noise? What sort?
It kind of sounded like
something crumbling.
[ALL gasp]
[LAVI shouts]
Run for it!
[LERO]
Lero!
[ALLEN]
The hallway!
[LAVI]
It's falling apart!
[LERO]
Lero! Lero!
[ALL shout]
[LAVI]
It just keeps going on and on!
Does this hallway ever end?
[CHAOZII grunts]
[ALLEN]
Chaozii!
[CHAOZII gasps]
Great job, Allen! Nice catch!
Lenalee, I have some flasks
of blood in my pocket
that Chomesuke gave to me.
I need you to
retrieve one for me.
[LENALEE]
Sure.
This?
[KRORY]
Pass it over.
[ALLEN grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
We're going to make a mad dash,
so hold on tight, you brats!
[ALLEN]
Krory.
[CHAOZII shouts]
[LERO grunts, shouts]
[CHAOZII] Why are you letting
that rat hitch a ride with us?
[LERO] Stop being
so mean to Lero!
[gasps]
There's a light up ahead!
[LAVI]
It's the end of the passage!
[KRORY grunts]
[LAVI shouts]
[ALL grunt]
Where are we?
A library?
Wherever we are, it's stable.
Which means we're in a part of
the Ark that hasn't
been downloaded.
[LERO]
Lero.
Finally, a moment to rest.
[JASDERO chuckles]
[DEVIT]
Up here, Exorcists.
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Welcome. I'm Devit.
I'm Jasdero! And together
we become Jasdevi!
[chuckles]
Jasdevi?
[LAVI] These two are even
weirder than the others.
Jasdevi. I knew it was you.
Instead of wasting time here,
shouldn't you be trying
to apprehend Cross?
[BOTH]
Shut your mouth!
[yelps]
Failed again, Lero?
In case you can't tell,
we're in a bad place
emotionally right now.
[LERO] What's that got to
do with anything, Lero?
[DEVIT]
Allen Walker!
[gasps]
It's not like we have anything
against you personally...
But we do have heaps of
resentment and bitterness
with Cross, so as his pupil
you'll have to answer for it!
[LERO sighs] So they're
taking it out on him, Lero.
[JASDERO, DEVIT grunt]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Heaven's punishment!
[ALLEN] Wait! What did you
say about General Cross?
[ALLEN gasps]
Watch out, Allen!
[ALLEN grunts]
Ouch!
They hit him.
But looks like the bullets
didn't do any damage.
[KRORY gasps]
What is an invoice?
It's a paper that says
you've got to pay.
[JASDERO laughs]
[KRORY gasps]
The pupil should pay for
his master's debt, right?
Load Blue Bomb!
They hit him!
Did the gun change power?
No. Not the weapon.
It's the bullets
that are unique.
[gasps]
[ALLEN] I see. So you're the
ones who left the traps for us.
You got it! He, he!
I'm gonna guess you're the
Noah who're after my master?
And since you've gone through
all this trouble to take your
anger out on me, I suspect
he's still alive and well.
Go Clown Belt!
[DEVIT grunts]
[JASDERO grunts]
[DEVIT, JASDERO grunt]
Allen!
So they're after you
'cause you know Cross.
Seems so. More importantly,
we have to be careful.
They're not firing
normal bullets.
Whatever ammo they're using,
it has some kind
of special ability.
[DEVIT, JASDERO grunt]
You know what? This is
getting kind of fun.
[JASDERO laughs] We haven't cut
loose in a long time! Ha, ha.
Tell me something, apprentice!
You think if we took
you as a hostage,
we could we lure
Cross out of hiding?
Are you kidding?
Wow Allen. Just how
cold-blooded is your master?
Even the Exorcists
don't trust Cross!
[BOTH laugh]
One time, he knocked
me unconscious
with a hammer to escape.
I assure you, he's more
threatening than you.
How horrible.
Well. How about a game?
The two of us versus you.
Better hope you're as good at
escaping as your master,
Allen Walker.
♪
[ALLEN] Let's be honest.
No one likes Master Cross.
But the twin Noah,
Devit and Jasdero,
have an especially fierce
grudge against him.
Makes me wonder what on
earth happened between them
and my Master.
On the next D.Gray-man:
"Debt Crisis."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[ROAD] Oh?
[ALLEN, LENALEE]
Hm?
Since Komui's not
here today, that means...
[BOTH]
It's time for some anarchy!
Chaos isn't allowed in school!
As class president,
I put it to a vote!
[STUDENTS]
We're with Lenalee!
[BOTH]
Huh? But we're in charge.