You are nothing.
[FO screams]
[AKUMA A laughs]
Walker.
What did you do?
Who are you?
I'm an Exorcist.
An Exorcist, is that so?
[AKUMA A]
In that case... Who is this?
Ah-ha.
I think I understand now.
Wal...ker.
Fo. I saw Bak crying.
That can't be right.
Well. Not really, but yeah.
Oh, Bak...
Houshin!
Summon!
Hey, Walker!
He still can't activate
his Innocence.
Uh! Fo!
Oh? Should I be
afraid of you now?
[VOICE]
Please...
Please. Love me.
Stop him.
I'm... I'm right here.
Please save me.
So you've been the one.
The one who's been
calling out to me.
[VOICE] You can see me,
and hear me, can't you?
[ALLEN]
Mm-hm.
[VOICE] Believe me, I never
wanted to take this form.
But please, please love me!
[ALLEN]
Uh...
[VOICE] You exist for our
sake, isn't that right?
Heh.
I do.
[AKUMA A] I'll wipe that
smile off your face!
[AKUMA A roars]
[splash]
[BAK]
Fo!
[footsteps]
[WONG]
Chief Bak!
[SHIFU]
Oh, no!
Stupid Bak. Why did...
Why'd you have to go
and let Walker escape?
Fo...
Sorry.
I couldn't get him to
bring out his power.
And then I...
I didn't buy very
much time either.
That's not true,
you did a great job.
It was more than enough.
Hold on.
Are you... crying?
You can't be--
Don't talk anymore.
I'll get you treatment, okay?
It looks like she
survived the attack.
This is the first time I've ever
seen the Chief get so emotional.
--[crash]
--[SHIFU] Huh?
Walker! Run away!
[AKUMA A roars]
I won't run!
I'm going to fight him!
Because it's my job
as an Exorcist!
An Exorcist's job.
But Walker...
[ALLEN] You guys have to hurry
up and get out of this place
right now! And take
Bak and Fo with you!
We can't leave you here!
You know that!
You should run while you've
got the chance, weakling!
[ALLEN grunting]
As I said,
my dark matter allows me to
make other matter decompose.
I can wipe away your existence
in the blink of an eye.
Now disappear!
[ALLEN] I'll fight
for the sake of Akuma,
and I'll live for Akuma!
[ALLEN]
That's why I'll never give up.
I started down this
path knowing that.
And then, I...
[AKUMA A grunts]
[ALLEN gasps]
Uh. His leg.
It's falling apart!
Oh, no.
[AKUMA A laughs]
Are you insane?
Why would you try to
fight in that condition?
Here you go!
[gasps] No!
[LO FWA gasps]
He'll kill him!
[ALLEN screaming]
Walker!
How much more can he take?
Whoa. If this keeps up...
Wal...ker...
[BAK]
Stop this, damn you!
You're too weak! Stop!
I have to. If I don't, then...
[FO groaning]
Fo!
Ha! Foolish girl.
When is she going to realize
that she doesn't have what
it takes to defeat me?
You'll pay for what
you did to Fo!
Houshin!
Ha!
[grunts]
Poor boy!
What makes you think a technique
like that would affect an Akuma?
[BAK growling]
[BAK gasps]
[BAK gasping]
Bak!
Now disappear for good.
Wal...ker...
[ALLEN]
Is this...
...how I'm going to disappear?
[ALLEN] I'll fight for Akuma,
and I'll live for Akuma.
That's what I decided.
[ALLEN] I kept walking...
and never stopped.
[ALLEN] Akuma were the only
things in this world
that were precious to me.
But somehow...
...I almost forgot how I felt.
When you close your eyes and try
to imagine what "the world" is.
What do you see?
[ALLEN] Those people
became so important to me
that I forgot about what
used to matter most.
You're right, Fo.
I live with Akuma.
And I live with my
comrades, too.
Both of those are precious.
They're both part of me.
[ALLEN]
I guess Akuma, and my friends,
all of them combined are
the guideposts for my life.
I can't abandon either one,
and I definitely can't
let it end like this.
No!
Please don't die!
[AKUMA A gasps]
[BOTH gasping]
What the hell?
What is this?
Incredible.
He's emitting an insane
amount of energy.
[ALLEN]
Innocence.
I finally understand.
[ALLEN]
My right arm is for humans.
[ALLEN] And my left arm
is for the Akuma.
Well now.
[AKUMA A grunting]
[ALLEN]
Humans and Akuma...
...I'll save them both!
Whatever that is,
it saved us just now.
It's a mask?
What happened?
Is that thing a human?
[AKUMA A]
Ha, ha!
Just how many of you
freaks are there?
[FO]
Uh?
It's Walker.
You're in my way!
It's time for you to disappear!
[roars]
[AKUMA A growls]
[FO, BAK gasp]
Now, the main event.
Decompose! [laughs]
--[BAK grunts]
--[FO whimpers]
[BAK]
I... I'm still alive.
[FO]
We survived, Bak.
[BAK gasps]
Walker's Innocence
is finally active.
That's crazy.
It repelled the threads
from that Akuma!
I'll break you
into little pieces!
Die!
[AKUMA A groaning]
[groaning continues]
[ALLEN]
Let's go.
[BOTH laughing]
[ALLEN]
Let's go...
...together.
[ALL gasp]
Walker... You...
No way.
Is that really him?
Finally!
Good job, kid.
[AKUMA A growls]
You little wretch.
[yelling]
This poor Akuma needs salvation.
Ha!
His left arm's back!
Go get 'em, Walker!
[ALLEN]
My right arm protects humans.
And my left arm protects Akuma.
May your soul rest in peace.
Let me ask you something Akuma.
Where did you plan to take me,
and who gave you the order
to take me there?
Sorry, kid. Can't tell you.
[laughs]
Unless you promise
to spare my life if I do.
That's fair enough.
Now tell me...
[laughing] Do you think
I was born yesterday?!
You're not gonna spare me!
Nice try though, clown boy!
I'm serious. I don't
want to hurt you.
I can help you.
I just want to save your soul.
[AKUMA A] Hold on, I thought you
were on the humans' side.
I am.
Well, half of me is.
But the other half is different.
That side wants to
help Akuma like you.
I will bring salvation
to this poor Akuma's soul.
Oh dear, what's this feeling?
Heh, heh, heh. Everything feels
so wonderful all of a sudden!
All right then.
I'll answer you.
It was one of the Noahs
who sent me here.
Sir Tyki Mikk, actually.
I can't help but wonder what's
going on in Edo right about now.
It's not just him.
Oh, no, four other
Noahs are there too,
and even the Earl himself!
Isn't that something?
Uh-oh.
Are you afraid now?
Thank you for that.
Now, take Noah's Ark.
You'll need to reach Edo
as soon as you possibly can.
Hurry.
I promise that it'll carry you
safely across the distance.
Why, Akuma?
[AKUMA A]
"Why"?
[ALLEN]
Yes.
Why would you share that
information with me?
[AKUMA A]
Because a Noah commanded me to--
Wait, no.
I wonder...
I don't know why, but suddenly
I feel so warm and peaceful.
Finally.
I'm saved.
It's been so long.
Thank you, Allen.
Goodnight, Akuma.
Walker...
[NARRATOR]
And so, in that moment,
Allen Walker was able to realize
and obtain his Innocence
in its truest form.
And it was chronicled
by the name...
...the clown of God.
Crown Clown.
[ALLEN] When Noah's Ark
appears unexpectedly,
the Asian Branch
devotes all its energy
to tackling the
mysterious phenomenon.
And now that I've got
my Innocence back,
there's something important
I have to do.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"The Name Chronicled."
Bring salvation to this
poor Akuma's soul!
[FO]
Stupid Bak.
I'm here. What?
[FO]
Nothing, nevermind.
[sighs] Okay then.
[FO]
Hey! Stupid Bak.
What now?
[FO]
Eh, just forget it.
Whatever...
[FO]
Stupid Bak!
[BAK groans] All right,
that's enough of that!
What'd you have to go
and hit me for?!
[FO]
Because I like you.
Huh?
[FO]
Sorry, I meant...
...I like hitting you!
[BAK growls]