[LENALEE gasps]
[ALLEN gasping]
[SUMAN DARK roars]
What am I looking at?
We're gonna get
you out of there!
Ready, Allen?
I'll try to remove him!
[gasping]
Help me, Mommy.
Don't let me die.
[gasps] Mommy. Help me.
[ALLEN grunting]
[screams]
[gasps]
[LENALEE]
Give me your hand!
[ALLEN]
Take the girl!
[LENALEE gasps]
[ALLEN screaming]
[ALLEN] Suman's emotions
are flowing through me.
Flooding into my own.
I can't take it!
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN]
So that's it. Suman.
You deserted your friends.
And begged the Akuma
to spare you.
You betrayed the Innocence,
didn't you?
It was your decision. You chose
to become a Fallen One.
It's trying to kill him.
His Innocence is
trying to kill him.
You're going to stop. Right now!
[ALLEN grunts] You can't
kill him! I won't let you!
Apostles, God,
all his creations!
I curse every living thing!
Destroy them all.
Let them face destruction!
What's happening?
We're going down.
[ALLEN]
A village!
Stop this, now! That's enough!
I curse you all!
I curse you all...!
We're headed for
the village, Suman!
[MALE VILLAGER gasps]
What's going on here?
What is that that thing?
It's coming this way!
Can you hear me?!
I curse you all!
I curse you all...!
Suman! You have to stop!
[screams]
[SUMAN DARK]
Damn you, Exorcist!
Stop trying to interfere!
Go back to hell
where you belong!
[ALLEN]
I'm not leaving!
If you don't stop,
you'll destroy that village
and I can't let that happen!
Please, Suman, don't do this!
Remember who you are!
We're Exorcists!
We fight to protect
innocent people! Now stop!
[SUMAN DARK growls]
Shut up! Shut up!
[ALLEN grunting]
[ALLEN]
So much power.
Hey! Suman, you have
to snap out of it!
Your soul is under attack!
Your Innocence is eating
you from the inside out!
You can't go on
like this for long.
If you do, your Innocence
will kill you!
Listen to me, Suman.
I can save you. I know I can,
but you have to help!
Fight against the
darkness, Suman!
You don't want
anyone to get hurt!
Don't give into it!
[SUMAN DARK growling]
Die!
[ALLEN groans]
It's feeding off of you,
don't you get it?
The more you destroy,
the more life you'll lose!
[SUMAN DARK]
Die!
[ALLEN groans] Stay with me,
Suman. You have to fight!
I'll save you.
I swear to you I will.
So you have to stay alive!
[SUMAN DARK groans]
[ALLEN gasps]
Shut your mouth!
[ALLEN screams]
Suman!
What-- What was that?
It looked like it crashed
in the mountains.
Wait! There it is!
Oh, no. It's headed this way.
[SUMAN DARK screams]
[VILLAGERS gasping, screaming]
[VILLAGERS scream]
[whimpering]
I'll get you out of there! Ahh!
Wow.
That guy's even more demonic
than we are, and we're Akuma.
[AKUMA B] Look at him scare
those little humans. Ha, ha, ha!
So, what? Should all
of us move in on him?
[AKUMA D] Not yet. This is
starting to get interesting.
Yeah. Let's hang back and
see how this plays out.
We can go after him once
the village is destroyed.
[AKUMA B]
Oh! Good plan!
[coughs]
[ALLEN panting]
I have to stop him
before it's too late!
Innocence! Release max power!
Activate!
[ALLEN yells]
[screams]
[ALLEN] I swore I'd save you!
I refuse to let you die!
I'm gonna hold on and
not let you go! Ahh!
[ALLEN]
No matter what.
You're gonna get
out of this alive.
[panting]
What now?
I don't know!
Is it over? Did it stop?
Why isn't it attacking anymore?
[LENALEE]
Can you repeat that?
Are you saying there's no hope?
[KOMUI] Yes. Once someone
becomes a Fallen One,
they can't be saved.
Suman... will not survive.
That's a lie.
[SUMAN] Help me. Please,
I don't wanna die!
[SUMAN groans]
Help me.
[SUMAN DARK roars]
[LENALEE]
I don't understand. Why?
[KOMUI] There isn't
anything anyone can do
once a person has
become a Fallen One.
Nothing can save them.
Nothing?
[KOMUI] There are only two ways
it can end for a Fallen One.
Either they keep destroying
until they use up
all their energy, and they die.
Or, they end up fighting with
something else, like an Akuma.
And it kills them.
In both scenarios the
result is the same.
A Fallen One cannot be saved.
It's impossible.
[LENALEE]
You're lying!
[KOMUI] No I'm not. Now calm
down and listen to me carefully.
What about Suman? What is
all of this Fallen One stuff?
It's bad. Innocence gone crazy,
and there's no cure.
When someone Falls, Innocence
takes control of their body...
...and destroys it.
Usually in less than a day.
[JOHNNY gasping]
Few know this.
Even the existence
of Fallen Ones
is a closely guarded secret.
But Suman. He's an Accommodator.
Why would his Innocence
do that to him?
Can't the order
help him somehow?
He and I...
Our rooms aren't that far
apart from one another.
So we're neighbors.
And sometimes he'd come over and
the two of us would play chess.
Right now I'm up,
38 games to 7.
My longest streak yet! He's,
uh, kind of a sore loser.
Didn't like that too much.
So when he saw me
in the mess hall,
sometimes he'd be
mad and ignore me.
But every time he came back
from one of his missions,
he'd come and see me
and start a new game.
Johnny...
[whimpers] I know we
weren't really friends.
He was just lonely.
The only thing he
wanted was company.
But even so,
what'll happen to him?
I told you. He's gonna die.
Once it's all over
and done with,
his Innocence will normalize and
return to its original state.
You must then collect
it quickly, Lenalee,
before the Akuma have the chance
to get their hands on it.
You can't be serious.
Komui?!
Are you suggesting we just
stand back and let him die?!
The Order wants you to
collect the Innocence.
That is your one
and only mission.
What if Suman's Innocence
is the Heart?
You understand what that means.
There are more important
things than one life.
But he's our friend!
[KOMUI]
Are you certain of that?
How do you know his
feelings haven't changed?
What are you trying to say?
This information is
still classified.
But there is a
strong possibility
that Suman betrayed the Order.
[sighs] I'm sure I don't need
to remind you of the incident
where over a hundred
Finders and Exorcists
were massacred while
in the line of duty.
[gasps]
Not long before it happened,
an Exorcist called in and asked
the Communication Section
about other agents
in the field.
He requested information
regarding active Finders
and Exorcists including their
locations and abilities.
[LENALEE gasps]
[KOMUI] Wireless Golems have
built-in security features.
They are assigned to
only one Exorcist.
If a Golem doesn't recognize
its owner's voiceprint,
it will block all
communications.
During the investigation,
we learned the Golem used
to contact headquarters
that day was Suman's.
Thus, we believe that
he made the call.
Most of the time,
Exorcists are away from branch
offices and out on assignment.
So it's not unusual
for them to call in
requesting backup
or an update.
Therefore, the Communication
Section gave the caller
the information he asked for
without checking
with Command first.
The attacks happened soon after.
No other Exorcist knew the
locations of all those killed.
But on the other hand,
we could be wrong.
Even if Suman had
the information,
we don't have proof he
gave it to the enemy.
But it remains possible
that he could have.
Now that he's become
a Fallen One,
it seems to confirm
our suspicions
about his involvement.
This is his punishment
for his crimes.
Suman betrayed us.
He betrayed the will of God.
[LENALEE] You're lying!
I don't believe you!
[cries] That's a lie.
You're wrong.
It's not true.
[ALLEN]
Suman, stop!
Stop this mindless destruction!
Please, Suman! Don't let
the Innocence control you!
[roars]
Listen to me!
I felt what you felt!
I know how badly
you wanted to live!
I know you loved someone!
I know you wanted
to go home to her!
[gasps]
[SUMAN DARK gasping]
[ALLEN] I saw a little
girl in your memories.
That's your daughter, isn't it?
I saw when you had
to say goodbye to her.
It was the last time
you were with her
before you left
to join the Order.
Someone help me.
Help me, please!
[ALLEN] I know that you never
wanted to join the Order!
I know you never wanted
to be an Exorcist!
[ALLEN]
But your little girl was sick.
And you needed money to pay
for her doctors and medicine.
So you became an
Exorcist to save her.
There's no shame in
not wanting to die!
Even though you left your family
believing you'd never see them,
you clung to the hope
that it might be possible!
And in the face of death
you missed them so much
you were willing to do anything!
[SUMAN]
Let me live. I beg you.
Please don't kill me.
I'll do anything you ask
if you spare my life.
I don't care what. Anything.
You hear me? Anything!
I don't wanna die!
I miss my family.
Desperately. I wanna go home!
Even though you surrendered.
Even though you gave up.
Even though you sold your soul!
In spite of it all, I know
that you still wanted to live.
Didn't you?!
[LENALEE cries]
[screaming]
[ALLEN]
He can't go on like this.
His Innocence is killing him.
I have no choice. I have
to separate him from it.
[ALLEN]
There's no other way.
He'll lose his arm, but
at least he won't die.
It's the only choice.
I believe he would want this.
Above all else he wants to live!
So it has to be done!
Here we go. Innocence, Activate!
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN gasping]
[ALLEN groaning, screaming]
It hurts. Why does it hurt?
What's wrong?
[screaming]
[ALLEN] Suman continues
to rain down destruction
while his body falls apart.
He's on the brink
of losing his life.
If I intend to save him,
I'm going to have to try
something different.
Next time on D.Gray-man :
"A Scream."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul!
I'll take my usua--
[ALLEN]
Jerry. Jerry! Did ya hear?
The Order said
they're gonna hold
a wanko soba eating contest!
And I figure if I wanna win it,
I better start practicing now.
So give me all
the soba you've got.
That's right, all of it!
I'm gonna eat it all by myself.
[KANDA]
Hey, short stack.
[ALLEN]
Hm? I know Kanda loves soba,
but you can make him
something else, right?
[KANDA]
Short stack!
Oh? Were you gonna practice
for the soba contest, too?
[KANDA growls]
How 'bout I take your head off?!
Best friends forever. Yep!