Oh no.
It isn't good. Right now,
part of the ship
is experiencing repeated
time recoveries.
It's coming from...
...above us.
The ship's deck
is being attacked!
[ESHI] I think I'll title this
one: "Corpse of an Exorcist"
[LAVI] Devouring Flame!
Direct Fire Stamp!
Dammit! I could've done
without those injuries!
New title:
[LAVI]
Huh?
[ESHI] "Why Does This Exorcist
Keep Recovering?"
There's no way.
You must be a Level Three.
[ESHI] I can tell you about
him, on one condition.
You agree to be a
model for my art.
[BOOKMAN gasps] You're...
You're a Level Three Akuma!
[gasps]
I title this...
"Old Man and the Moon"
[LAVI]
No.
[LAVI grunts]
Old man! Come on! Please!
Wake up!
[LAVI]
Old man!
[ESHI chuckles]
Please. Please work.
It has to. Please.
[CREW grunting]
Those who can move,
get to your positions!
[MIRANDA panting]
[KRORY] I don't like what
I'm seeing out there.
[LENALEE]
I'm really worried about them.
[KRORY gasps]
[LENALEE]
What is it?
[KRORY] Just now I had
this sinking feeling...
[MIRANDA gasping]
We have a problem!
Lavi's traveling too
far away from the ship!
When he leaves my coverage,
his injuries are going
to return immediately!
And now he's in
the middle of combat.
There has to be
something we can do.
Leave the Akuma to me.
[MIRANDA]
You can't go alone!
[KRORY]
You sure you'll be all right?
I will.
Lenalee, promise
you'll come back.
Yes. I'll see you again.
[KRORY]
Uh.
[LENALEE]
Innocence Activate!
Please be careful.
[LENALEE] You need to
head back to the ship!
[LAVI]
Lenalee! Hold on!
Don't go!
His power's different from
Akuma we've fought before!
He's a Level Three!
You can't fight him alone!
[LAVI groaning]
[LAVI] My injuries. Why are
they coming back now?
I must be too far away
from the ship. Dammit.
Uh. Lenaleee!
[ESHI chuckles]
[ESHI]
I'll title you...
[LENALEE grunts]
[ESHI]
Huh?
[LENALEE yells]
[ESHI]
You're fast.
[LENALEE yells]
[LENALEE gasping]
[LAVI]
Lenalee!
Don't worry about me, Lavi.
I'll take care of this.
[LAVI gasps]
Go back and protect
the ship while I'm gone.
[LENALEE] I'll catch up
with all of you later.
There's no way
I'm leaving her.
[BOOKMAN]
Lavi. Go back to the ship.
[LAVI gasps]
He's not the only
one we have to fight.
There are more of them up there.
Just beyond the clouds.
[LAVI]
What?
[CREW screaming]
[CREW K screaming]
[screams]
[MIRANDA gasping]
[MIRANDA gasps]
[CREW groaning]
[MIRANDA cries]
[SAILOR A]
You all right, Exorcist?
Looks like you
didn't get hit. Good.
What about you?
Don't you understand?
If you're injured, you'll die
when time goes back to normal!
[SAILOR A chuckles]
We know. But we've already been
hit several times before.
You see, we've got nothing
left to lose by shielding you.
We aren't going to survive
this voyage anyway.
Might as well be of
use and protect you.
[MIRANDA cries]
[KRORY yells]
To think I'm fighting
a defensive battle!
The cowards fight from
behind the clouds!
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Krorykins!
Fire Stamp!
[KRORY]
I should have said this earlier,
but, don't call me
Krorykins, eye patch!
Heh. Sorry, Count.
He won't do it again.
Survivors! Head to the furnace!
[CREW panting]
[CREW grunting]
Engines at full power!
Heaven Compass, Divine
Protection Needles!
East Crime! Stop the Akuma!
Forgive me,
but this helm's too heavy for
you to steer alone, Master.
Mahoja. Thank you, my friend.
[ANITA] As long as you're by
my side, we'll reach Japan.
[LAVI] Reversed Thunderbolt!
Krory! Come give me a hand!
[KRORY]
You ready? Go!
[LAVI yells]
Heaven Stamp!
[KRORY]
Did it work?
I think we can take that as
definite "no"! Aim next time!
Jeez. I thought I could take
'em out just shooting randomly.
[LENALEE] Burden. Water-surface
kick technique. Water Shackles.
[growls]
[LENALEE grunting]
[gasps]
[groans]
[yelps]
[ESHI chuckles]
[LENALEE gasping]
[ESHI groans]
[ESHI grunts]
[LENALEE groaning]
What the..? [gasping]
[ESHI chuckles]
[LENALEE whimpers]
Not one of you will
see the daylight again.
What is this? An earthquake?
I've never seen one
like this before.
[MAHOJA] The damn rudder.
It's refusing to budge.
[CREW T grunting]
[CREW U]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[MAHOJA, ANITA grunt]
Ahh!
[ESHI chuckles]
I'm sinking.
My Dark Boots are still working
So, that means... It's him.
[ESHI] You're not the
only one who'll drown.
Before the night is through,
the sea will have swallowed
its fill of souls.
[LENALEE gasping]
What did you do to the ship?
[ESHI chuckles] You will be
reunited with your friends
very soon, and spend
eternity with them.
After you fall to
the dark depths below.
[LENALEE]
What do you mean?
We're going down.
But none of the attacks
pierced the hull.
[MIRANDA]
This isn't right.
The Time Record should still
be working on the ship
without any problems!
[MIRANDA gasping]
What are these things?
I can't move.
This is my dark matter ability.
I use it to control the
gravity of my victims.
You didn't know, but every
time you received an attack,
dark matter was added
to the damage.
Weighing you down gradually
until you began to
sink into the water.
Not so fast anymore
are you, Exorcist?
This is the end for you.
[ESHI]
There's no escaping me.
[SAILORS chattering]
[LENALEE groaning]
[screams]
Keep struggling to
escape your fate.
Even if you know it won't
make any difference.
It will fill you with
a false sense of hope.
For a short while at least.
[LENALEE groaning]
[CREW grunt]
[inahles]
Keeping climbing! Hang in there!
[MAHOJA grunts]
All right! You got
any bright ideas?
[KRORY] This must be the doing
of that Akuma from earlier!
Then that means our only
chance is defeating him!
And we gotta do it quick,
otherwise this
voyage is history!
[LAVI grunts]
Lenalee.
[gasping]
[LENALEE gasping]
[gasping continues]
[LENALEE gasps]
[LENALEE groaning]
[JOHNNY gasps]
What's wrong? You okay, Chief?
[KOMUI gasping]
[JOHNNY]
Chief?
I... I'm fine now.
I lost my balance.
It's strange. I thought I
heard a voice cry out to me.
[KOMUI]
Lenalee...
[LENALEE groans]
[ESHI] Title: "The Maiden Who
Has Fallen Into Darkness."
[ALLEN] Eshi's ability
to control gravity
continues to drag
Lenalee lower.
Further into the dark,
impenetrable depths
of the ocean.
As she loses consciousness,
a vision comes to her.
On the next. D. Gray-Man :
"Maiden Who Has Fallen
into Darkness."
Huh. So, someone wrote
in requesting to know
how D. Gray-Man Character
names are pronounced?
I'll do this once.
So, you better listen as though
your life depended on it.
"Yu Kanda. Lenalee Lee. Lavi.
Allen Walker. Komui Lee.
Reever. Bookman. Miranda. Krory.
Noise Marie Cross Marian.
Froi Tiedoll. Winters Socalo.
Klaud Nine. Hevlaska.
Sumon Dark. Daisya Barry.
Kevin Yeagar. Jerry.
Millennium Earl. Lero.
Road. Tyki Mikk.
Skinn Bolic. Devit.
Jasdero. Lulu Bell. Timcanpy."
Etcetera. Etcetera...
[gasping]
Don't forget about the people
in the Asian Branch, Kanda!
Huh?!
[ALLEN laughs]
[LENALEE]
So evil.
[KANDA]
Damn you short stack!
[ALLEN whimpers]
[KANDA growls]