Oh, Eliade!
How they feel can't be helped...
Don't you see, Arystar...?
They are human,
and you are a vampire.
My dearest Eliade...
I will love you...
With all that I have...
Let's live here in this castle
forever, you and I alone...
Yes...
Forever... and ever...
Pentacles... on the
surface of the ground.
No mistake...
traces of Akuma blood.
Agreed...
Could this be a graveyard
for... for Akuma?
Allen, the pentacles are
showing on this one, too!
I'm afraid we're going
to find the pentacles
on every one of these graves.
I don't know...
But I do think...
There's a lot more going
on here than vampires.
I can't believe
they're still alive...
They're like a couple
of stubborn cockroaches.
If I ignore this it will
only be a matter of time
until they figure
out what's going on
and try to take Arystar
away from the castle.
That's why, under no
circumstances
can I let them leave...
Unless, of course,
they're both inside coffins.
I wonder what that
shaking was earlier.
Dear Grandfather...
Do you remember what you
said to me before you died...?
You said that the only place
I would ever find happiness
is here in this castle,
tending to our flowers.
And now it seems as
though following this path
is the only choice with
which I've been left.
Grandfather...
I've become a real vampire, the
one thing I've tried to avoid...
The villagers all fear me...
Too afraid of what
I might do to them,
they all avoid even
being in my presence.
I realize my fate is
now set in stone...
I will live here
until death takes me.
But why am I crying...?
For I will always have
my dear Eliade by my side.
Grandfather.
Is this a curse you've
placed upon me...?
You knew I'd always yearned
for the outside world...
And even as a child I made it
my goal to break your very will,
but it seems as if
you've changed me...
Turned me into a
monster to ensure
that I never venture beyond
these walls in my lifetime.
Oh... Arystar,
I've been looking for you!
Eliade.
Oh my, what's wrong?
There are men outside
claiming to be exorcists!
They snuck into the castle
and want to murder you...!
They tried to attack
me but I got away.
They did what?
They even burned
all the flowers...
The ones you love at the
bottom of the staircase.
Of course...!
That must've been what I felt...
Those bastards...!
How dare they destroy the
flowers Grandfather gave me.
Please Arystar...
defend this castle...
You must fight them.
But... I... don't know.
If you don't stand up and
do something about this,
they will kill you...
You're a vampire...
You're already
their natural enemy.
Please drink my blood...
now...
Eliade...
The exorcists are
strong, Arystar.
You won't stand a
chance against them
in the state
you're in right now.
But if you drink my blood,
you should be able to
transform into a vampire
more powerful than
they could ever imagine.
But promise me
you'll be careful...
You need only drink a little...
Just don't... kill me in
the process, my love...
Eliade.
Arystar... Do it.
Then we can live the rest
of our lives in peace...
You're all I have
in this world...
Eliade.
You know I noticed
something earlier.
Why don't you tell me
while you keep shoveling?
I've smelt the scent of those
carnivorous flowers before...
I think they triggered
a distant memory...
It was from awhile
ago with Master Cross.
He was growing flowers
that smelled just like that.
Really?
The only thing is the flower
he was growing was in a pot.
But I'm certain it
was the same kind.
So you think the flowers were
planted by General Cross?
All I think is that it's
possible the two are related.
I think I found it.
Just as we thought...
It's an Akuma.
Every one of these
graves contains an Akuma.
The pentacles we've
seen on the ground
must have appeared once
each of the bodies decayed
and then leaked the
virus into the soil.
Do you realize what
this means, Lavi...?
All of the villagers Count Krory
has attacked have been Akuma.
Of course...
If the Count is only attacking
Akuma and not human beings...
Then this mission
is no longer just
a cut-and-dry
vampire elimination...
Krory must be something else.
That's right...
If Krory isn't a vampire
like we originally thought...
Lavi!
You two have made
me very angry...
Count Krory is no vampire...!
He's actually a...
He's a...!
I can't believe his speed!
Count Krory...!
Please hear me out!
You afraid you're going to end
up like your little friend?!
He disarmed the
weapon on his left arm.
All I want to do is talk.
The bodies of these
villagers in those graves.
They're Akuma, not human...
Were you aware of that?
In fact, do you even know the
difference between the two?
Akuma?
Count Arystar Krory...
Are you a vampire,
or are you something else?
Mind your own business...
Got it?
Your blood tastes disgusting.
Yeah...?
That must be because
it's human blood.
Human?
Don't kid yourself...
You're a monster
and you know it.
Akuma and vampires have
nothing to do with me...
Do you hear me my boy...!
I'm just a simple man who
lives inside this castle.
With the lovely Eliade...
Just the two of us living
here undisturbed for eternity!
And I promise...
I'll kill those
who get in my way...
Including you!
That was quick.
You shouldn't ever
turn your back on me...
It takes a lot
to keep me down...
So I'll just kick your ass now
so you and I can chat later.
Interesting.
Take this!
My head is killing me.
I must have slammed into that
wall pretty hard or something...
What the heck...?
Either I'm hallucinating
or there are stars
circling around my head...
Geez Tim...
Quit it.
Playing hard to get, huh...
Well... It sounds
like Lavi is feeling better...
I guess I should go back him up.
Where am I?
What is this?
Ugh, my head's still spinning.
What the...
Is this some kind
of secret room?
What is that?!
You're pretty tough, aren't ya?
Could that shadow be a...
It's gone...
Maybe I really am
hallucinating after all.
It's you...
Hello...
If it isn't the
gray-haired boy from before.
Seriously...
Pathetically busting into
a woman's private room
of secrecy is so uncouth...
I believe someone could use
a lesson in proper manners.
Aww...
It looks like you were bitten.
I know...
I was hoping it
would heal by now.
Why are you doing
this...? Let me go.
Oh Arystar...
I knew I couldn't trust you to
take care of this little twerp.
How annoying...
I let him suck my blood and he
still couldn't finish the job...
Must I do everything
all by myself?
Well so be it...
Luckily for me I have the
time to kill you on my own,
you exorcist scum!
Where is she getting
all this strength?!
What's wrong boy?
Aren't you going to fight back?
I feel dizzy and like
I'm getting a fever.
It must be the effects
from where I was bitten.
I'm so sleepy.
No response?
Maybe Arystar was more
effective than I thought...
Come on, can't you
put up a little fight?
No...
I must resist the
urge to fall asleep...
If I don't she'll kill me...!
Snap out of it, Allen!
Please stop...
I'm not fighting back
because I don't have reason to.
I also have no intentions of...
Eliminating
Arystar Krory either...
Because he isn't a...
Akuma, and he's not a vampire.
The villagers Arystar killed...
Every one of them were Akuma...
It's possible that
Krory could be one of us,
a full-fledged Exorcist.
If that turns out to be true
we will escort him home with us.
You really think
he's an Exorcist?
You must be suffering
from brain damage!
He's just a vampire, silly...
And he will...
stay with me... forever!
He and I will live
here for eternity...
Huh?
I will never let you
steal Arystar from me...
Got it?!
You know where you
belong, Exorcist?
In a grave.
And I'm going to make
that happen for you.
That move actually surprised me.
Just as I thought...
It looks like you
really are one of us.
Excuse me?
Every one of those villagers
you attacked was an Akuma...
The only kind of human
that can survive a vampire bite
is a Parasite Type
Accommodator...
Which is what you are...
Follow me...
Afraid all the evidence
is there, Krory...
And it confirms that
you are an Exorcist,
whether you like it or not.
Oh yeah...?
You think I'm that naïve?
No...
You were just going
after Akuma's blood
without realizing it because
the consciousness that is
within Innocence will
hunt Akuma on its own,
with or without
your permission...
In other words,
you're beginning to
synchronize with Innocence.
Ya know...
You seem to get a kick
out of hunting Akuma...
If you join my friend and I,
you could hunt all you want.
I'm not interested.
I thought you'd say that.
I recall you wanted to wait
to have a conversation
until after you beat me.
Well... That was my
original plan...
But seeing that you're much
stronger than I anticipated...
I thought it'd be a
good idea to talk first.
We're beyond diplomacy now
so I won't be holding back...
So just give me your
answer once you wake up...
Fang-boy.
Don't you sound confident...
Maybe now I'll break a sweat...
You'll see...
Just you wait.
Innocence... Level Two Release!
Arystar and I had
planned on living together
here in this castle,
completely isolated from the
world outside our gates...
Forever, that is before you
and your friend showed up.
When I introduced you
to my flowers last night
it was a warning to turn
your back and leave...
You had your chance, but now
you're mine to play with...
A good idea would be
to chop off your head
and place it on a stake
in front of the castle...
As a reminder to all fools
who think they can hassle
us and get away with it.
I would gain honor
amongst the ranks
for taking off
this Exorcist's head
and most importantly the
Earl would praise me for it.
More than anything...
Arystar and
I could be together...
Forever!
You little faker...!
Is he unconscious or not?
Is he possessed...?
His left arm is
moving all by itself...
But how?
I have returned, Allen...
The darkness is back.
Mana...
Do you remember the last time
I couldn't see out
of my left eye...?
I decided that even if
I lost that ability forever,
I'd still grow up strong and
train to join the Black Order...
Just like an exorcist...
I will be prepared...
Mana!
Now Allen...
you must go deeper...
...into the realm
of black... and white.
Thanks Mana.
Your arm...
It's...
Eliade...
You are an Akuma.
Now I see...
You're the Akuma
we saw last night.
Your eye is finally healed.
Black and white...
My world has finally returned.
You see my true form...
That's right...
I take back what
I said before...
I do have reason to fight now.
There's the beautiful
Akuma known as Eliade
and Krory, the supposed
vampire who can defeat Akuma...
The true meaning
behind their relationship
has finally become clear.
Next time on D. Gray-man:
"The Truth About Eliade."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.