Maker of Eden, activate!
Garden of Embrace!
All right, Lau Jimin. Activate!
[KLAUD]
Go!
You ready to come out and play?
Time for Judgment.
[GIANT AKUMA E]
Exorcists.
[laughing]
Not Tup.
[BAK]
Johnny!
Where do you think you're going?
You're in no shape to run.
I'll find you.
They're taking him.
They're taking my friend away.
[ALLEN] It's faint, but my eye
is reacting to something.
Were there Akuma that survived?
The reading's so weak,
I can't tell if it's
just my imagination.
[TIEDOLL]
Ugh. What a terrible stench.
[MARIE]
Command center.
This is Noise Marie
in Lab 5. Do you copy?
We've stopped the Akuma
invasion on Headquarters.
Can that radio
reach the outside?
From what I heard,
Chief's Bak's latest
model should be able
to punch through the
Ark's magnetic field.
Let's see.
Command center, do you copy?
Chief Komui. This is Lab 5.
[KOMUI] This is command center.
We read you. Go ahead.
What is the condition
of Laboratory 5?
[MARIE] Several dozen
Science Section members
are seriously injured.
The dead Akuma are giving off
large amounts of noxious gas.
Breathing conditions and
visibility are limited.
Best you cover your mouth
and protect your lungs.
These fumes are
poisonous to breathe.
We'll turn on the ventilation.
What about the enemy portal?
[MARIE] Two gateways remain.
Neither show signs of closing.
Thank you for the report.
Standby, Marie. And protect
Miranda, understood?
General Cross. Do you copy?
I read you.
[KOMUI] I'm going to have
Miranda deactivate her power
and return the egg
to normal time.
The hell are you
talking about?
We only have one
option available.
I want you to destroy the egg.
[ROUVELIER]
Don't be brash, Chief Komui.
I can't let you do that.
Are you blind to the
value the egg possesses?
It's too late to save it.
It's already been
transferred to their Ark.
The Time Record only turns
time back temporarily.
But it can't erase events
that have already transpired.
Which leaves us
with two choices.
Either we destroy it,
or let the Earl have it back.
There's no time to waste.
We've got to evacuate.
Get your people to the
highest floor, Reever.
[REEVER] No. I'm fine.
Everyone else, go upstairs.
[MARVIN]
Section Leader?
You can't!
Even if my subordinates
were transformed,
they're under my command
and my responsibility.
I saw them being taken
to the farthest gate.
Someone has to go save them.
All right then, Reever.
I'm going with you.
[REEVER]
No, Allen.
[MARVIN]
I'm coming too.
Count me in.
You guys.
A word, Inspector Link.
I require your skills
for a secret task.
Your abilities haven't
gotten rusty, have they?
[LULU BELL]
Damn humans.
[CROSS] To destroy the
egg with a single blow,
Klaud, Socalo, and I have
to synchronize our attacks
to hit the target
at the same time.
Then again, there's no guarantee
we'll actually be
able to break it.
After all, this is dark matter
we're talking about.
Do what you can, General.
[CROSS]
Very well.
Ready whenever you are, Miranda.
Yes, General.
[MARIE]
Hm?
Where's that noise coming from?
[gasps]
Miranda!
Noel Organon!
[MARIE]
My strings cut right through it!
What the hell is that thing?
Is it even alive?
We've met her before.
The Noah of Lust has the ability
to take any form she wants.
The egg belongs to the Noah!
It's coming with me.
[MIRANDA]
I can't breathe!
I wonder if your ability
stops when you die.
Let's find out, shall we?
The egg is sinking!
That means time must be
moving forward again!
Do you really think you
stand a chance against me?
Do you really think we'd let
the egg return to the Earl?
Right.
[SOCALO]
Madness! Cremation Dance!
Pathetic.
Bastard!
That killed the large
Akuma with one blow.
But it had no
effect on the Noah!
[KLAUD] Our turn, Lau Jimin!
Destroy the egg!
You realize you're wasting time.
This time we got her!
[KLAUD]
She was just liquid.
Can she change her
form that quickly?
Arrow of Original Sin.
General Cross's attack
should've been a direct hit.
And it didn't even
scratch the egg?
Its power is remarkable!
Still hasn't cracked.
Let's change that.
[yells]
I don't know what,
but something's
breaking the lab apart.
[ALLEN]
That's Miranda!
Don't worry about us, Allen!
Just find a way to save her!
Got it!
Better hurry,
or we'll end up getting
dragged into the battle!
What're you waiting for?
I swear, these newborns
always take their sweet time!
Now, in you go!
Got you, Tup.
That is you.
You're still in there.
[chuckles]
I've been watching upstairs
this entire time.
Don't you worry.
There's no way I was gonna let
the Earl take away my friend.
[SKULL C chuckles]
What's this idiot's deal?
Doesn't he realize that
puppet belongs to us now?
I order you to dispose
of this garbage, newborn!
[JOHNNY]
Tup?
Don't go!
Wait! You can't leave!
[JOHNNY]
Your name's Tup!
Don't leave!
Please don't go!
No, come back! Don't go, Tup!
[AKUMA A]
Human. Human.
[JOHNNY screaming]
It's still alive?
Damn!
She isn't allowing any
of our Generals' attacks
to get past her defense!
Well, the logical choice would
be focus on defeating the Noah
instead of destroying the egg.
There just happens to be
one problem with that plan!
Currently the enemy has Miranda
absorbed inside her body!
[LULU BELL]
Almost there.
Just need to hold off their
attacks a bit longer.
You're not going anywhere!
Little worm!
[LULU BELL gasps]
[LULU BELL]
The egg's breaking!
It's no use! I can't stop it!
Time's up.
We can hold back our attacks
because of Miranda,
or end this right now.
[SOCALO] Looks like
the only way we can win
is by taking out the Noah
and the egg all at once.
Destroying the egg takes
precedence over everything else.
You can't be serious!
Generals, please!
Activate Long-Range
Form, Lau Jimin!
[KLAUD]
Armor-Piercing Cannon! Lau Guns!
[CROSS]
Judgment's level: Atonement.
Increasing power
to triple damage.
[LULU BELL] The Exorcists are
raising their energy levels!
They plan on fighting?
[LULU BELL]
But I've got a bargaining chip.
Sure you want to
do this, Exorcists?
You'd go so far as to
kill one of your comrades
in order to stop me?
And such a pretty one. Surely
her power is of value to you.
The fiend is using Miranda's
body as a shield for the egg!
[LULU BELL] Are you
willing to destroy the egg
if it means murdering
one of your own?
[SOCALO]
She's an Exorcist. Like us.
I'm sure the girl's prepared to
die for a cause she believes in.
She won't have to.
[gasps]
I can't hold on!
[ORDER MEMBERS yelling]
Come in, Generals!
Marie! Miranda?
[DOCTOR A]
Everyone, get down!
[LENALEE screams]
What's going on?
Hey! Are you all right?
Hold on while I move
this out of the way!
Just hang on!
[KANDA]
I'll take this!
Wow! That was amazing!
This blade needs sharpening.
[LULU BELL]
Finally, safe at last.
I need to hurry and
get back to my Master.
It's not too late to repair you.
Damn those Generals.
[gasps]
[LULU BELL]
What is that white lump?
You bastard!
You truly are a heartless
man, Cross Marian.
You knew he was
down there all along.
But you kept on firing anyway.
Didn't hit him.
In any case, he is a
Transcendent One.
Stop this! If you damage
it anymore, it'll--!
Allen Walker!
I'll kill you for this!
You're a terrible Master.
I did it because I had
faith in you, my apprentice.
The portal's vanished.
[KOMUI] General Cross!
Can you hear me?
General? Give me
a status report!
The Noah retreated?
And the egg?
You were able to destroy it?
[ORDER MEMBERS celebrating]
[BOOKMAN]
Hm?
Is she going to live?
[BOOKMAN] There's no need to
worry. She's just unconscious.
What a relief.
Allen, wait.
I have to check on
Reever and the others.
I'm worried about them.
[giggling]
[giggling continues]
[ALLEN]
A new, bizarre Akuma appears
after feasting on the lives of
Science Section Members.
As it continues to evolve,
what terrifying form
will finally emerge?
On the next D.Gray-man:
"Level Four."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[LENALEE, MIRANDA chuckling]
It's so pretty.
All right, short stack.
What're you plannin'
on doin' with that?
Oh.
I just wanted to show my friend
Kanda some harmless sparklers.
[KANDA]
Tch.