[MILLENNIUM EARL grunts]
[LENALEE gasps]
[EVIL SPIRITS laughing]
[LENALEE whimpers]
[LENALEE gasping]
[MILLENNIUM EARL laughing]
[LENALEE whimpering, screaming]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Why, good evening.
What a surprise to
see you again...
...Allen Walker!
[ALLEN]
Hmph.
Hello, Earl. Good evening.
[MILLENNIUM EARL] You know,
you're becoming a real pain
in my neck. Showing up at
the most inopportune times
and ruining my plans.
[ALLEN]
It's over.
You can't have Lenalee!
[MILLENNIUM EARL laughs] Cling
to her as much as you want.
Makes things easier for me,
since neither of you
are getting out alive!
[BOTH gasp]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
The two of you can die together!
[ALLEN grunts]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Huh?
I won't let you lay
a hand on her again!
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Huh?
[ALLEN yells]
[LENALEE whimpering]
My legs...
Because of the crystallization,
they won't move.
[LENALEE]
Allen...
Heh, heh, heh. I'm comin'
for you, my dear.
Huh?
What the...?
You're persistence is tiresome.
Fight me, Earl!
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
If you insist!
[ALLEN grunts]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Well, so serious.
You know what you remind
me of? A white face clown.
Chasing after the
gleeful Auguste.
Is that what you think is
happening, silly child?
[ALLEN] Guess that makes
you the Auguste.
If it's my job to stop the fool,
then I'm happy to oblige!
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Hm?
I won't stand by while you
make everyone suffer!
I came back to the battlefield
to put a stop to you
once and for all!
[MILLENNIUM EARL yells]
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN groans]
[MILLENNIUM EARL grunts]
[MILLENNIUM EARL groans]
There's only one way to
save humans and Akuma!
You're the one not
leaving this place alive!
Cross Grave!
[MILLENNIUM EARL screams]
[ALLEN grunts]
[MILLENNIUM EARL chuckles]
[gasps]
Looks like the performance has
concluded, but we'll meet again.
And hopefully next time we won't
put our audience to sleep.
Lenalee!
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Perhaps she'll
join us for the encore.
That is, if this isn't
the final show.
[gasps]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Take a bow!
[LAVI grunting, coughing]
Did you see what happened?
[LAVI]
Some kind of explosion.
[ALLEN]
Lenalee!
What? Allen?
No. Come on.
Get it together, Lavi.
[LAVI]
Man...
What is going on here?
[gasps] An Akuma?
Lavi!
There's no way!
It's Allen!
I can't get Lenalee to wake up.
[LAVI]
What's wrong?
Oh yeah. I've seen this before.
Hey, but don't worry.
Her condition shouldn't
be life threatening.
[ALLEN]
Really? Are you sure?
[LAVI]
I'm positive.
What a relief.
This has happened before?
One other time
that I know about.
After the crystallization,
she was so exhausted that--
[KANDA]
So you thought you could escape.
[LAVI, ALLEN]
Huh?
[KANDA]
Die!
[ALLEN yelps]
Hey! Kanda!
What?!
Short Stack?
The name's Allen.
Why are you here?
I should be asking
you the same thing.
I was following a Noah
with curly hair.
Hey, Lavi.
Do you have any idea
where he went?
Come to think of it, that
muscly guy I was fighting
vanished, too.
The Noah are gone.
What happened to them?
[ALLEN]
Don't give me that face!
You can't pretend like I'm
the one who let them escape!
If you want the truth,
I might as well tell you.
The Noah got away
'cause you're slow.
What did you say to me?
I coulda sworn you were calling
me slow just now, Short Stack.
Even though you were
the last to show up.
How many times do I need to
tell you, my name's Allen.
That's right, I forgot.
You can't help that you're a
bit slow in the head as well.
You've got some nerve.
I'm gonna show you how fast
I can be, Short Stack!
Let's go! Draw your weapon!
I'll slice off your hair
and make wigs out of it!
I think black hair would fetch a
higher price on the wig market.
[KANDA] I'll be generous and
leave one strand on your head.
That's enough, kids.
Settle down.
Marie's right.
You guys should be carrying
on like old times!
[BOTH]
We are. Don't interrupt.
[LAVI, MARIE]
Uh...!
That person standing next
to Kanda looks like...
It can't be.
It's Allen Walker.
Just as I thought, he's alive.
[TIEDOLL]
With one slight difference.
The form of his Innocence
has changed.
A great deal has happened in
such a short amount of time.
Hm... Looks like we'll
need to get caught up
before we go any further.
[TYKI] Just when things
were getting fun.
Was it really necessary to
withdraw, Lord Millennium?
That Exorcist girl could have
been the Heart, you know.
We should have taken
her out then and there.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
So heavy.
You might want to consider
cutting back on the sweets,
Skinn, my darling.
[TYKI]
You're not even listening.
Man. What a pain.
[ROAD]
The Ark data transfer
will be complete in less
than four hours, Earl.
[TYKI]
Huh?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Oh, Road. A job well done.
How can I repay you?
I want a year's supply of candy.
That's my standard rate.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
It's a deal.
Speakin' of jobs, I can think of
someone who failed at theirs.
Your target seems to have come
back from the grave, Tyki.
[TYKI]
Huh?
He's alive? Left arm and all?
You sure it was him?
Intact and so full of life!
He did a splendid job
at gettin' in my way.
[TYKI]
Oh, boy...
Hey! What cha talkin' about?
[MILLENNIUM EARL] Just how
unreliable Tyki is at his work.
Duh.
Heh! Mm?
[sniffing]
So Tyki. Did you change
your cigarette brand?
[TYKI]
No. Why are you so interested?
Thinking of taking up smoking?
[ROAD]
No reason.
Wait a minute.
Lord Millennium. Where's Lero?
[chickens clucking]
[BOTH]
Uh...
[JASDERO]
Um, Devit.
Is that Cross?
[DEVIT]
Where did he go?!
[banging]
[TIEDOLL] Altered Akuma, Lenalee
could be the Great Heart,
the Crowned Clown.
Okay. Let's see if I'm following
everything we discussed.
The goals of the Cross Unit
are to meet up with Marian,
and destroy the Akuma
manufacturing plant.
Is that correct?
So far.
[TIEDOLL] However, my objective
for coming to Japan
is to find new Accommodators.
I hate to say this after
we've had the fortune
of running into each other,
but, you should know,
I have absolutely no intention
of aiding Marian Cross.
The man considers everyone
but himself as tools.
Puppets to be used
in his machinations.
You were supposed to serve
as his guard but instead he
used you and his altered Akuma
as decoys. Pawns in his scheme.
You can understand why
I'm quite hesitant
to cooperate with the man.
[ALLEN]
I wonder if there's anyone
who doesn't hate my master.
If I may, I would like
to propose a suggestion
for you and your group.
Go ahead.
I feel your most important
duty at this time
is to leave Japan immediately.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
You can't be serious.
You're telling us to stop
fighting and go back home?
There's a time and place to
strike the Millennium Earl,
but it's not here or now.
As apostles, your
most important duty
at this moment is to stay alive.
As of now, the only
Exorcists alive in the world
are Hevlaska at the Order,
Socalo, Klaud Nine,
Marian, and lastly,
the nine of us here.
There are no more.
We can't afford to lose
anymore Exorcists.
I feel the best solution in this
situation is to retreat.
So the choices are give
up or keep going, right?
[exhales]
I'm sorry to tell you, General,
but it's not the first
time we've heard this.
We were already warned by
a former comrade of ours.
You should turn back around,
you'll only slow
the General down.
Japan is already under
the Earl's control.
If you go there,
you'll most likely die.
And you know,
we thought about it.
Then Sleeping Beauty
here spoke up.
Let's move on.
There's no turning back now.
It'd be a betrayal to everyone
who sacrificed their life
so we could get this far.
I won't let that happen.
[LAVI]
So we made up our minds.
To keep moving forward,
no matter how much the odds
were stacked against us.
[KRORY cries]
Lavi speaks the truth.
We'll keep going.
We won't give up!
Yeah! Count us in!
And you share these
sentiments, Allen?
I do.
Nothing's going to stop
me from moving forward.
[sighs] Very well.
If that's the case, I won't
bring up the subject again.
The journey to this
point was perilous.
But you should know, only
more hardships await you.
A winding path
lined with thorns.
[LAVI sighs]
This is it, Krory.
Won't be long.
Once Lenalee wakes up and
is able to get on her feet,
we'll be back on the road again.
Uh? What's the matter?
I nearly forgot Lenalee's words.
How could they've slipped
my mind so easily?
We can't turn back now,
or the lives of everyone
who helped forged this path
will be forfeit.
Arystar.
[KRORY] And I include Chomesuke
along with them.
As do I. If we don't
press onward,
we'll never be able to
avenge our lost friends.
[ALLEN]
Can you forgive me?
I'm sorry for disappearing
so suddenly.
And, also...
[ALLEN]
...failing Suman Dark.
I couldn't save him...
[gasps]
You're awake!
Is that... you?
I'm sorry. For everything.
[LENALEE]
What?
[ALLEN]
I have so much to apologize for.
[LENALEE]
There's nothing to forgive.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[LENALEE]
You're worried about Suman?
[ALLEN gasps]
[LENALEE]
Everything's all right.
He didn't die in vain.
Don't you realize in the
end you saved his heart?
[ALLEN gasps]
It was all because of you.
Thank you for rescuing his soul.
Welcome back, Allen.
I missed you.
It's good to be back.
And this time, I'm staying.
[BOOKMAN] Looks like
you're feeling better.
[LENALEE, ALLEN]
Uh!
What's this? Are those
tears in your eyes?
No! I, I just...
I seem to remember you
crying on the ship, Lavi.
What?! That never happened!
[ALLEN]
Hold up. You were crying, too?
[LAVI] Like I already told you,
it never happened!
Yeah. You were probably
bawling your eyes out.
You weren't even there!
How would you know?!
[CHAOZII]
Nice and tight!
Got everything packed,
and ready to go!
[shattering]
[MAOSA] I think you got
a little problem there.
[KIE] How did you tie
the sack upside down?
[CHAOZII]
Uh? What the heck?
Maybe I should have
used a different knot.
[KIE] I don't think your choice
of knot was the problem.
[LAVI humming]
Lavi.
[LAVI]
Hm? What's up?
You told General Tiedoll
you wished to continue
on this journey.
That you wanted to see it
through until the end.
That's right.
What's the problem?
Just wanted to know if it was
as the Bookman successor,
or rather, if you believe you're
an Exorcist of the Black Order.
How many times do I have to
remind you of your place?
I haven't forgotten.
You sure do worry
a lot, old man.
You ought to learn to
relax once in a while.
What do you say we get
back to everyone, huh?
[BOOKMAN grunts]
[KANDA] You're seriously
gonna go through with this?
[KRORY] Lenalee said
she can move again.
We'll be resuming
our course shortly.
[KANDA sighs]
What a bunch of lunatics.
Yeah, well, I guess you're all
gonna die somewhere, right?
Uh! What's your problem?
We won't know for
certain until we try.
Wha--?!
[KANDA growls]
[ALLEN]
He's right.
Our fates' aren't
written in stone.
[ALLEN grunts]
[MIRANDA] Do you want me to
reverse time for you, Chaozii?
[GROUP chattering]
[ALLEN] No matter how difficult
the road ahead lies,
I have to keep walking forward.
But this time,
I have my friends.
--[LENALEE groans]
--[thud]
[ALLEN gasps]
Come on... Get a grip, Lenalee.
No. I'm all right.
I have to stand on my own.
[ALLEN]
Lenalee...
You're not alone.
We're all here.
Let's find my master, together.
[LENALEE]
Together.
[gasps]
There you are, Lero!
[LENALEE gasping]
[LENALEE screams]
Lenalee!
[gasps]
[KANDA growls]
[ALLEN] Without warning, a hole
to another dimension appears.
And Lenalee is dragged
through to the other side.
And what's that in
the sky above Edo?
Some kind of mysterious
glowing object.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"A Key and Noah's Doors!"
Bring salvation to this
poor Akuma's soul!
Soba noodles again, Kanda?
Wrong!
What're you eating then?
Breakfast, mori soba!
Lunch, zaru soba!
And now mori soba!
What?! That's the same
dish every meal!
It's not!
Soba? No thanks!
Yakiniku for me!
Um. I think pears
are pretty good.
Pudding's my vice!
Chocolate cake for the win!
Eliade.