[NARRATOR] Suman Dark.
Parasite type Exorcist.
Joined the Black order
five years ago.
He belonged to General
Winters Socalo's guard unit,
which was attacked in
the Agra District of India
by the Noah Tyki Mikk.
His fellow Exorcists, Kazarna
Rido and Charcar Lavong,
were killed during the battle.
However, Suman Dark's
whereabouts
have been unknown
since the attack.
I've never seen
this many before!
[BOTH grunt]
[CREW E grunting]
[BOOKMAN]
Hm?
[KRORY grunts]
Why are they flying
past the ship?
They're just ignoring us?
What gives?
Who the hell do they think they
are, running from a fight?!
[screams]
[AKUMA A]
Did I break your concentration?
This is no time
for daydreaming!
[LENALEE] The Sound Shackles
turn those vibrations
into footholds, allowing the
wielder to move at Sonic Speed!
[AKUMA A]
What the...?
[LENALEE]
Take this!
[ALLEN screaming]
Allen grab my hand!
Lenalee!
[LENALEE gasps]
[gasps]
[SUMAN DARK roars]
What am I looking at?
Why are they attacking it?
Their job... Is that
what they meant?
Their goal was to
destroy this thing?
[SUMAN DARK roars]
[gasps] His face...
It's Suman.
[LENALEE screams]
What? Why did you scream?
Are you hurt?
He's a Fallen One.
[gasps]
[LENALEE] Someone who failed
to become an apostle.
[LAB HEAD A] It would appear
he's lost the ability to hear.
We're free to discuss
the procedure openly
in his presence, gentlemen.
[LAB HEAD B] What was his
previous synchronization rate?
[LAB HEAD C]
Regrettably,
we didn't measure a
number worth reporting.
[LAB HEAD D] Each experiment
causes his body functions
to deteriorate further.
I'm starting to have doubts
whether the procedure
will work unless the subject
is an Accommodator.
[LAB HEAD A] This test may
prove to be the final one.
[LAB HEAD B] We can't give up
now. It's just a matter of time.
Beside, he's a close relative
of one of the Exorcists.
[LAB HEAD C]
True. Also, let's not forget
it was the subject's own desire
to undergo the process.
[gasps]
[LAB HEAD A]
Enough discussion.
It's time. Let's begin.
[LAB HEAD B]
Hevlaska.
Implant Innocence
in him one more time.
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[screams]
[LAB HEAD C] It's no good!
This is his limit.
It's too dangerous to continue!
Stop the experiment!
[LAB HEAD A] He's come this far.
We can't stop now.
Keep going, Hevlaska!
Please... Stop this.
[LAB HEAD B]
Synchronize, damn it!
This is wrong!
[screaming continues]
[gasps]
[HEVLASKA] Foolish humans.
A waste of time.
Innocence. Synchronization.
Only an Accommodator
chosen by God can endure it.
All others will fail.
[LAB HEAD A]
Damn. Another failure.
Another Fallen One.
[LENALEE cries]
[LENALEE]
I've seen this before.
When someone's sync rate with
Innocence is zero or less,
it rejects them.
If a non-Accommodator tries
to synchronize with Innocence
by force, they're punished.
They become a Fallen One.
They say it's a sin
carried by a non-apostle
for betraying the will of God.
It's forbidden now,
but I've witnessed it.
When I was young,
I saw the experiments
performed at the Order.
[gasps]
This abuse of Innocence.
Trying to create Exorcists
from non-Accommodators.
I'll never forget the boy
from the experiment.
He looked like that.
[LENALEE] The same figure
as Suman. But why?
It doesn't make any sense.
Suman was an Accommodator.
He was an Exorcist, like us.
[ALLEN]
His name was Suman Dark?
Yes. He was a Parasite
Type Accomodator.
The same exact type as you are.
He's been in the Black
Order for five years
under General Socalo's unit.
I heard they were
attacked the other day
and Suman went missing.
But what happened?
It doesn't make any sense!
How did he become a Fallen One?
[ALLEN] I think only one
person knows the answer.
[INNOCENCE] I won't allow it.
I won't let you run away.
There's no escape for you.
[SUMAN DARK grunts, screams]
Suman!
He vaporized all the Akuma!
I've never seen destructive
power like this!
[KRORY grunts]
[LAVI yells]
Dammit! There's no end to them!
What's keeping
Allen and Lenalee?
Do I look psychic?
[LAVI] Look at the sky over
there. It's burning red.
Everyone hurry and get the
injured below to medical!
Look at that.
[MAHOJA]
Akuma! Another swarm?
The hell...? What's
going on over there?
[groaning]
[ALLEN]
Now what?
He's starting to destroy
indiscriminately.
If we don't do something--
We have to save him.
Allen. There's still time
to save Suman! I know it!
It's not too late?
I asked Hevlaska about
the experiment I witnessed.
I can't remember the
number of times I begged.
But she wouldn't reveal
anything to me.
I never learned what
happened to that boy
after he became a Fallen One.
I tried so hard to,
but I couldn't.
[LENALEE] Please, Allen.
We have to save him.
[ALLEN]
Mm-hm.
[AKUMA A]
The Earl wasn't kidding.
It's just like he said.
This guy is dangerous.
[AKUMA B] On the bright side,
we're gonna get his Innocence.
[AKUMA C]
That's right.
Remember there are tons of us
Akuma and only one of him.
[LENALEE]
Waltz. Misty Wind!
[AKUMA D]
What?! Exorcists?!
[ALLEN gasps]
Suman!
[AKUMA F]
What the hell is going on?
[LENALEE]
Suman!
Don't get close, Lenalee!
We shouldn't step anywhere
near this portal!
Suman! It's Lenalee!
Can you hear me? Give me a sign!
We're gonna get you
out of there!
Ready, Allen?
I'll try to remove him!
[gasps]
Help me, mommy.
Don't let me die.
Uh! Mommy. Help me.
[ALLEN grunts]
[yells]
[gasping]
[ALLEN grunting]
[LENALEE]
Give me your hand!
[ALLEN gasps]
Take the girl!
[LENALEE gasps]
Allen! No!
[ALLEN]
Where am I?
[groans] My head!
What's going on?!
[ALLEN screams]
[ALLEN] Suman's emotions
are flowing through me.
Flooding into my own.
[ALLEN] Stop it! My skull
is going to explode!
I can't take it!
[LENALEE]
What should I do?
The girl. She isn't breathing!
Akuma!
[AKUMA G]
Keep attacking!
[AKUMA H]
Take his Innocence!
[LENALEE]
I can't save her if I stay here!
I have to find her
treatment. But...
...Allen.
[LENALEE]
I have to help this girl.
Hold on, Allen! I won't be long.
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN]
Suman. What did you do?
[SUMAN]
No! Stay away!
I don't wanna die! Someone!
[LENALEE]
Suman was an Accommodator.
How did he become a Fallen One?
[SUMAN]
I don't wanna die like this!
I want to keep living!
[ALLEN] So that's it. Suman.
You deserted your friends.
And begged the Akuma
to spare you.
[ALLEN] You betrayed
the Innocence, didn't you?
It was your decision. You chose
to become a Fallen One.
[SUMAN DARK screams]
[LENALEE]
Innocence Release.
Level Two!
Acoustic Kick Technique.
Sound Shackles!
[LENALEE gasps]
[ALLEN]
This sensation.
He must've released another
energy wave against the Akuma!
[shrieking]
What are these?
They're shrieking.
Is this Suman screaming
out in pain?
Then he is suffering.
I wonder... Could this be
the will of the Innocence?
It wants him in agony?
[ALLEN] There's something
about the destructive force
Suman possesses. The
quantity is unusual.
Is it possible.
Is the Innocence boosting its
power by devouring his body
and shooting out that energy?
I never learned what
happened to that boy
after he became a Fallen One.
I tried so hard to,
but I couldn't.
[GHASTLY VOICES shrieking]
[ALLEN]
I have to figure this out.
Huh?
Wait a minute...
It's trying to kill him.
His Innocence is
trying to kill him.
It's trying to punish the
sinner. Like God himself.
[GHASTLY VOICES shriek]
[ALLEN]
Stop it.
Hey, Innocence! Are you
listening? You can't do this!
You're going to stop. Right now!
[grunts] You can't kill him!
I won't let you!
[ALLEN] That object...
Is this Suman's Innocence?
[ALLEN groaning]
[ALLEN]
I'm outside. It spat me out.
His Innocence must have
rejected me. Now's my chance.
[ALLEN grunts]
Hang in there, Suman!
Don't you die! And don't
think of giving up!
Do you hear me?!
I'm pulling you out
of there! Hang on!
[SUMAN DARK screams]
[SUMAN DARK] Who's there?
Who are you supposed to be?
What do you want?
There you are.
[SUMAN DARK]
I curse you! I curse you all!
I curse you all! I curse
you all! I curse you all!
I curse you all...!
Don't say that!
I'm an Exorcist, like you!
I'm your comrade!
Apostles, God,
all his creations!
I curse every living thing!
Destroy them all.
Let them face destruction!
[ALLEN grunts]
What's happening?
We're going down.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
A village!
She's not breathing. Nurse!
Prepare to resuscitate!
[NURSE A]
Yes, Doctor.
Is she going to survive?
Just leave her to us!
Don't worry.
[door creaks]
[LENALEE]
Oh. Doctor!
How is she?
[DOCTOR A]
Heh.
She's pulled out of her coma.
And her breathing's
finally stabilized.
The best thing now
is to let her rest.
Thank you for saving her!
[door creaks]
Stop this, now!
That's enough!
I curse you all!
I curse you all...!
We're headed for
the village! Suman!
[SUMAN DARK] I curse you all!
I curse you all!
Listen to me!
You don't want to do this!
I curse you all!
Wake up!
I curse you all! I curse
you all! I curse you all!
Anything and everything.
Face destruction!
[ALLEN] As Suman's life
dwindles to nothingness,
he promises to destroy
everything in his path.
I have no choice but to
take a gamble on him.
On the next D. Gray-Man :
"The Beginning of
the Night of the End."
Bring salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul.
Give me the usual.
[ALLEN]
Hey, Jerry!
I think I'm gonna start with a
rice omelet, mapo tofu, mapo
eggplant, chicken tomato curry,
naan, meat pie, nasi goreng,
tom yum goong, egg soup, takana
fried rice, lamb steak with
French fries, jambalaya, dango
dumplings and maybe some...
[KANDA]
Hey, short stack.
[ALLEN] Oh, and Kanda would like
a short stack of soba noodles.
[KANDA]
Short stack!
Wait. I've never heard of
a short stack of
soba noodles, Kanda.
[KANDA growls]
You! You're the short stack!
These two are best friends. Yep.