All units be advised
that a swarm of Akuma
have appeared in
the mountains...
From the direction
they're traveling;
they're headed to Barcelona!
Everyone be careful!
Hurry up...! You've got
to find the General!
Get moving...! The Akuma
will be here by nightfall!
What's the situation
in the other zones?
Still no word
from the port, sir...
We're completely out of
reinforcements to send.
Then we'll go ourselves.
I'm with the Finders
from Germany...
My name's Devon.
Right...
Thanks for coming, we can
use all the help we can get...
For starters...
The bay...
Take your unit and
get down there...
Keep the area under control.
Yes, sir!
Get whoever you can
and set up a perimeter...
No one in this
village is allowed in
or out until morning...!
Is that understood?
Yes, sir!
Hurry, run...!
Once it's closed, it stays
closed until tomorrow!
All right...!
Close it!
Hey, Dad. Are we there yet?
No, son. Not yet.
Don't worry... At this
rate we'll be in Vilanova
by morning at the latest.
No way...!
I feel like we've been
on the road forever!
I thought we'd be there by lunch
so we could go somewhere
in town to eat!
Dad! Tellima!
Somebody's out here!
Right over there!
Maybe he's a shepherd.
If he's a shepherd,
where are all his sheep?
What an absolutely
wonderful view from here.
He must be crazy or he
wouldn't wear those clothes.
They are weird.
Akuma, huh?
They passed this way
earlier this morning...
Which means we have
to pick up the pace
if we want to catch up to them.
Get down!
Ow ow ow ow...!
What are you doing?!
You see that?
Looks like it's
coming from the shore.
Let's go.
Right.
Come on... Hurry up!
That you, Kanda and Daisya?
Oh, it's you.
Here I was worrying about
what could be
taking you so long...
I should've known you'd be
slacking off somewhere...
I swore not to rest
'til we found you!
Daisya...
Shut up.
What do you hear?
A hundred...
Two hundred...
There are more than I can count
and I can count pretty high...
But there's a lot of them.
They're miles ahead of us...
They'll probably make it
to Barcelona by nightfall.
Whoa...!
There's no way we'll
make it by nightfall,
I don't care how fast we run!
How bout the General?
It's hard to say...
Hold on...
I think he's near there, too.
Then, dammit, let's go!
Wait.
Ta-da!
I almost forgot we
could get there by sea!
Way to go, Marie!
Let's get going.
Right.
Hey...!
Wait for me...!
You guys...! Hold on!
General Tiedoll should
be here by now.
Captain!
Very well, then...
That'll be all for now.
Yes, sir.
Men...
I just received word
that the army of Akuma
will be closing
in on us shortly.
Unfortunately, we
still haven't been able
to locate General Tiedoll...
But, in order to protect
the citizens of Barcelona,
we have no choice but to try
to hold the enemy
back ourselves.
Exorcists have been dispatched
to our location for support ...
Our only hope is to keep
the Akuma at bay
until they arrive...
It won't be easy but we don't
have any other options...
We'll do what has to be done.
So here's the plan...
I want all barrier units to
set up along the north gate
and await further instruction.
Right.
All other units, return
to your posts and stand by.
Right!
Guess it's back to
this life for now...
Well, don't these
look delicious?
Thank you very much.
Thank you, sir...
I'm shutting down
the shop early today,
so take another if you like.
Don't mind if I do...
I'll certainly need the energy
for the trip I'm about to take.
Is that so...?
Where are you going
to hide until then?
What are you talking about?
Some very important
people went around
telling everyone
to find someplace safe
to hide for the night.
That's why every merchant
in town is closing up early.
I'll keep an eye out
for trouble, thank you.
You really don't
get it, do you...?
Might as well take another apple
for that journey of yours.
Thanks again.
Papa says you must be
pretty thirsty, Mister...
So here... I brought
you some wine.
Ah... Thank you.
Hey, Mister... You can
draw anything, huh?
That depends.
Do you have anything
specific in mind?
I don't know...
Wait! How about
the city of Barcelona?
Ah... Is Barcelona where
you're all headed now?
Tonight we're going to
be staying in Vilanova...
Barcelona is tomorrow.
The beautiful
city of Barcelona...
If I remember correctly,
it looks something like this.
They're here!
Here they come!
Contain them!
Where do we stand?
There are two
more on the right...
No, wait!
Looks like they're
stopping here... and...
There's three
approaching from the left!
No!
They've stopped moving, too!
Don't let your guard down...!
We may not be able to
destroy these Akuma...
But we can hold them back
until reinforcements arrive!
What now?
Oh my god...!
They're coming up
from under the ground!
Get down!
They've broken
through the barrier!
Dammit.
All units...! Look sharp...!
The Akuma have
broken the perimeter...!
Stand your ground!
Yes, sir!
Let's go... Come on...!
Everyone
back to your post...
City Hall Unit's wiped
out...! Please advise!
Central Square Unit's been
almost completely annihilated!
The Akuma are closing
in on the marketplace!
All units that can
still fight, will fight!
Survivors of the attacked units,
make your way to the historic
district and find shelter!
Captain...!
We gotta find a way out!
There isn't a way out...
The Akuma have us trapped here.
This is Devon Unit
at the harbor district!
Send backup...!
We're completely surrounded!
We have no more units to send...
I'm sorry.
Looks like this is it.
But sir--!
Why can't you guys just learn
to start playing nice with us!
They all exploded!
Look!
They're finally here!
Innocence... Activate!
Netherworld Creature Indicate!
All right, I'm done
playing nice...
Charity bell...! Shoot!
The Verse... of the Saint.
Shoot!
I think we're all gonna be okay!
Demons will appear?
Yeah...
I've heard rumors from some
of the other traveling merchants
that demons have been popping
up all around Barcelona lately.
That's why Papa thought
it would be better
if we all stayed in Vilanova
for the night, where it's safe.
It may turn out to be
nothing, but it doesn't hurt
being a little cautious
until we're sure.
It's possible... that
there are demons nearby.
Are you going somewhere, Mister?
Yes...
I suddenly remembered something
very important I have to do.
Those demons that Papa
was telling us about...
It's about them, isn't it?
You should stay here
with Papa and us!
Ruben is right!
I didn't want to frighten
you by mentioning it,
but those demons
might be looking for me.
The last thing I want is to
cause trouble for your family,
but that's exactly what
you'll get if I stay...
You understand, don't you?
You're pretty old so
you should be careful...
If you see a demon,
run the other way!
That's good advice...
Be safe you two...
I'll be saying an
extra special prayer
that those demons
don't ever find you!
Yeah, me too!
Well, there goes that
whole stick-together,
there's-safety-in-numbers plan.
I had no idea there'd
be so many of them...
They just keep coming.
Yeah.
Aw, man.
Anybody else starving?
Daisya... You're breaking up.
I assume you both found
good spots to lay low?
I found a place about
three kilometers east
of that big,
crazy-looking tower.
Let me think...
I'd say I'm about five
kilometers to the west of it.
I'm in the southern
part of the city.
Great...
This is shaping up
to be one long night.
I hear Akuma in every direction.
Still no telling how many.
This whole city is
crawling with them!
Let's try to meet up...
Stay within ten kilometers,
and use our Golems to
track each other's location.
Then why doesn't Old Man Marie
just sit tight while us young
bucks go track him down?
When will you be here?
Expect us by dawn.
Okay, then!
Innocence... Activate!
Shoot!
You'll need a bigger
bullet to destroy me...
It's adorable, though.
Ta-da!
No...! What did you do to me?
It might be small but its
got it where it counts...
Destroying enemies from
the inside with sound waves.
Enjoy your short life as a bell.
He's done it again...
Why does the
Millennium Earl insist
we meet so far off
the beaten path?
Almost forgot about this one.
Ta-da!
Good evening... Exorcist.
Would you look at
that, a human...!
You wouldn't happen to
be an Akuma in disguise?
No...
Not exactly.
What's a human doing in a
dangerous place like this,
if you don't mind me asking?
Your name...
What should I call you?
It's Daisya...
My name's Daisya Barry.
You're not the one.
This doesn't concern
you, my friend.
Now if you don't mind,
I really should be going...
See you around...
So sorry...
But I can't shake the feeling
that you're no ordinary human.
How about you tell me a
little bit about yourself?
So much for self-restraint.
You see...
I only have so much patience...
Yes... Yes...
But that can't be...! Of course.
Yes, I understand.
You look upset,
is there something wrong?
Come on, we should hurry.
Why was the Black Order
contacting you here?
They wanted us to be
aware that armies of Akuma
from all over the world
have started mobilizing.
They say every Akuma
in southern Europe
is now heading towards
Barcelona... Fast.
Barcelona?
Remember Devon and the Finders
we met on the way to Spain?
He said they were
going to Barcelona!
Then that's exactly
where we're going, too!
Right!
I'm really going
to enjoy killing you.
Daisya?
What the...? Dammit!
You say something, Daisya...?
Are you there?
The city of Barcelona has
turned into a battlefield.
The fight between Tyki from
the Clan of Noah and Daisya,
Exorcist of the
Black Order, begins.
On the next episode of
D. Gray-man: "Silent Coffins."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!