[ROAD] Who cares
what this sword can do
if you're not really hitting me?
Come on. If you don't
know anything about me,
then how are you
ever gonna beat me?
[OTHER LAVI gasps]
And I'm not holding back!
Fire Stamp!
[LERO screams]
[ROAD gasps]
[LAVI]
Too real for you?
Then how about an attack from
that dream world of yours?
[ROAD] I'm impressed you
figured out my disguise.
Well, of course. You do seem to
have a thing for Allen, so...
[ROAD] It's over. You'll never
become the next Bookman.
[LAVI] I didn't
want to do this,
but it's my best
course of action.
[LERO]
Mistress Road's hurt, lero!
He attacked himself.
Lavi... Lavi!
You'll die! You have to stop!
I just don't understand.
I thought you were number 49.
You're supposed
to be just like me.
Identical in every way.
But look at you.
Why aren't you
like the other 48?
What makes you
act so differently
from your previous incarnates?
You're having so
much trouble, 49.
You're torturing
yourself. For what?
Becoming a Bookman!
That's what's important!
But no! You'd rather fight
for your temporary friends!
Humans are a
worthless species
that do nothing but
start wars! Am I wrong?
Your allegiance should be
with the Bookman Clan first!
We can't let our emotions
get in the way of our job!
[LAVI]
Time changes things.
At first, I had no faith
in human beings.
They lived and died in a
world of unending conflict.
I wanted to think I
was better than them.
So... Do you have the answers?
The reason why we
Bookmen even exist?
Or how come human beings
are always creating wars?
Fighting each other?
How do you expect me
to know that?
You think I have any answers?
I've had many names
in this life.
You represent 1 through 48.
Lavi is my 49th.
But we're the same.
It was you who asked
those questions.
You were the one
that started changing.
You need to get out
of here as much as I do.
[LAVI] We can't find
the answers if we stay.
[LENALEE grunts]
Wake up, dammit!
[LENALEE screams]
Lavi!
[ALLEN gasps]
Crown Clown! Return!
[ALLEN grunts]
It's Allen!
Please! Save him!
Save Lavi!
[ALLEN yells]
Come on! Break through!
[ALLEN]
Lavi!
[ALLEN yells]
Yeah, right!
You think I'm
gonna let you die?
[ALLEN]
Lavi!
Lavi! Lavi!
Grab my hand!
You and I are
the same person...
[CHAOZII, LENALEE gasp]
[ROAD] So you
managed to get out.
A promise is a promise.
Looks like you win this battle.
Lavi. Junior Bookman.
[CHAOZII] Wh... What
happened to the flames?
They're gone!
Where are they?
[LENALEE]
Lavi... Allen...
Huh? Is it over, lero?
But then...
Where's Mistress Road, lero?
[LERO yells]
M-Mistress Road!
No. It can't be, lero. She can't
be dead. Road can't be dead!
[CHAOZII]
Huh?
The barrier gave way.
Then, that must mean
Lavi beat Road.
[LENALEE] But where
is he? And Allen?
[LENALEE gasps]
Are you there?
Say something!
[CHAOZII, LENALEE gasp]
[ALLEN, LAVI yell, cough]
[CHAOZII]
They both survived!
[ALLEN, LAVI yell]
Oh, man! It hurts to breathe!
[LAVI laughs]
[LAVI]
We're alive.
[ALLEN] Sorry for
inconveniencing you!
[LAVI] Heh. You're reckless.
You know that, Allen?
[ALLEN] Gimme a break.
Find reckless in the dictionary,
you'll see your picture!
[LAVI coughs, laughs]
I don't know what happened.
But when I woke up,
I was on fire!
The old man will probably
yell at me for this.
But I feel pretty
good right now.
[LENALEE]
Lavi!
Hey, Lenalee!
Give you a scare?
A scare? What do
you think, idiot?
[LAVI screams]
[LAVI grunts]
Careful. Lenalee's got what
you would call tough love.
[LENALEE]
You had me so worried!
I'm sorry about that. Really.
[ROAD laughs]
M-M-Mistress Road?
She's alive?
[ROAD chuckles]
A... A... Allen.
[ALL gasp]
Don't go, lero!
Don't leave, Mistress Road!
A... A... Allen.
[ALL gasp]
Mistress Road? Lero!
Whoa. What happened to her?
Did you hear the way she
whispered your name, Allen?
She really liked you.
Seriously, what was going on
between the two of you?
[LAVI groans]
Let's get one thing straight.
There was nothing
going on between us.
[LAVI]
What's the big idea?
Hitting me when I'm
completely covered in burns?!
[ALLEN] Yeah?
And whose fault is that?
[LAVI] That doesn't
matter, jerk!
[CHAOZII]
Guys! Please stop!
[LENALEE] I'm kind of curious.
Now that Road disappeared...
Does that mean the exit
she created in the tower
vanished as well?
[ALL scream]
Lavi! No time to waste!
Go through the ceiling
and see if it's there!
Yeah! You got it!
[LAVI] I'll take a look
and make sure it's safe!
If everything checks out, I'll
come back and pull you guys up!
Right.
We're counting on you!
[LAVI]
Extend!
Another tremor.
It won't be long until
this place collapses.
[CHAOZII yelps]
How are your
injuries, Chaozii?
It's nothing.
Let's take a rest.
Hope the door's there.
I'm ready to get out.
Yeah.
[ALLEN] Based on the shaking,
we've probably got half an hour.
Kanda... Krory...
[LENALEE] Hey, Allen.
If there is a portal,
you are going through with us?
[ALLEN]
Huh?
Eh... You got me.
What you mean is, "yes"!
Ouch. That was a
mean right hook.
You know, Lenalee,
you've gotten more violent
since you lost
the use of your legs.
[LENALEE]
Stop joking!
Kanda and Krory must've
gotten held up somewhere,
and I'm not leaving without
finding them. There's still time
for me to go back and search
the Ark before it disintegrates.
I'll look too.
[ALLEN] No, you guys go
ahead and wait outside.
Allen.
I'm the most mobile one in the
group, so it makes total sense.
Hm!
I know what I'm asking of you
is hard, but understand.
This really is for the best.
[LENALEE] How can you
be so heartless?
You're smiling?
After what you just told me?
You wear that
expression on your face
even though you know it'd
kill us if we lost you.
Honestly. It wasn't
that difficult
for me to figure out
what you were thinking.
Because if I was
in your position,
I know I'd do the same.
I'd go back and look
for our missing friends.
[LENALEE]
All I want...
...is for all of us to
go back home, together.
All right. Talk about
a change of luck!
Guess we're okay.
Hey! The portal's still up here!
Just hold onto the handle
and I'll pull you guys up!
Oh, wait.
That's not gonna work.
Allen, since Lenalee
and Chaozii are injured,
you're gonna need to carry
them up along with you!
Okay. You ready?
I'm sorry I'm so heavy.
Don't worry.
I'll be all right.
You're sure about this?
Yep. Hold on and whatever
you do, don't let go.
[LERO]
Lero!
Why aren't you
coming to help, Earl?
Why did you abandon us, lero?
[ALLEN]
Tyki Mikk...
Right! Let's get going!
This portal could disappear at
any minute! No time to waste!
[LENALEE, CHAOZII]
Mm.
Allen! Let's hurry!
[ALLEN] We're bringing
Tyki Mikk and Lero.
[LENALEE, LAVI gasp]
[CHAOZII]
Huh?
You've lost your mind.
You can't be serious.
His inner Noah is gone.
Which makes Tyki Mikk
an ordinary human now.
Do you remember when we
first met him, Lavi?
[ALLEN] He wasn't
alone on the train.
He was traveling with
a group of friends.
There's a chance
they're waiting for him.
It just wouldn't be right
to let him die here all alone.
Hey, I don't have
a problem with it.
But, Allen...
You know what the Order
would do if they found out
you helped them. A Noah?
[CHAOZII]
What do you mean "help"?
You're saying that after all we
endured, you didn't kill him?
I chose to let him live.
[CHAOZII] But why? They're
in league with the Akuma.
Did you forget how they
killed Anita? Mahoja?
How they murdered nearly
all of my shipmates?
And here you are, helping
him. Helping a Noah!
You betray the sacrifice
they made for you!
If you save him,
then you're my enemy!
--Chaozii.
--My enemy!
In my eyes that makes you
no different than an Akuma!
Chaozii! Move!
[CHAOZII gasps]
What happened?
Say something, Allen!
Don't... Don't get closer!
[ALLEN moans]
[CHAOZII shudders]
[ALLEN screams]
[LAVI]
Allen!
[LENALEE]
Let go of him!
[LAVI] Allen! Damn!
It dragged him down there!
What the hell was that thing?
[LENALEE]
Allen, can you hear me?
Why did... Why'd you save me
after the things I said?
[ALLEN]
Chaozii! Move!
Why would you rescue me?
I refuse! I'm not gonna
lose another comrade!
Exorcist, hold on!
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN] No... The door.
Our only way out.
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN pants]
[ALLEN gasps]
Who are you? Tyki?
But that's impossible.
I destroyed your Noah.
What is going on?
Answer me. What are you?
[ALLEN] Are you Tyki Mikk...
or something else?
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN]
What is this feeling?
[ALLEN] I sense the power
of the Noah within Tyki Mikk.
The air I breathe...
It's cold as death.
[ALLEN]
I thought...
I don't like this.
I had destroyed it.
This terrible feeling.
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN] Tell me what's
going on! Say something!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
His blood... It's pitch black.
[TYKI screams]
[ALLEN gasps]
His body's changing?
[TYKI screams]
Lero! Where are you,
Lord Earl?
Why aren't you here
to save Lero?
[TYKI screams]
[ALL gasp]
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN] Tyki Mikk's Noah
has fully awakened,
transforming him
into a demonic knight.
A dark warrior
possessing such ferocity
his very essence threatens
to eclipse our hope.
On the next D. Gray-man,
"Black Carnival."
Bring forth salvation
to this poor Akuma's soul!
[LERO] So who can answer
the problem, lero?
What? Not a single
student in here, lero?
Hey, Allen. I'm sorry
I ate all your dumplings.
I forgive you, Lavi.
Thanks, buddy.
On that note,
I'm the one who stole
and ate your lunch
the other day.
[LAVI]
Ah--?!
And it was delicious, too!
Oh, yeah? Fire Stamp!
--[LENALEE] Huh?
--[LERO] Lero?
What's going on out here?
It probably
wasn't a good idea
to use your fire stamp
in a hallway.