[ALLEN grunting]
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Well, so serious.
You know what you remind
me of? A white face clown,
chasing after the
gleeful Auguste.
Is that what you think is
happening, silly child?
You're awake.
Is that... you?
I'm sorry. For everything.
[LENALEE]
What?
[ALLEN] I have so much
to apologize for.
[LENALEE]
There's nothing to forgive.
Everything's all right.
He didn't die in vain.
Don't you realize in the
end you saved his heart?
It was all because of you.
Thank you for rescuing his soul.
Welcome back, Allen.
I missed you.
It's good to be back.
And this time, I'm staying.
[LENALEE gasping]
[BOTH gasp]
[KANDA growls]
[KRORY growls]
[ALL gasping]
No! Lenalee!
You'll fall in!
Ah! Lavi! Help!
The Noah are after her!
[TIEDOLL]
Quick! Stop them!
[KIE]
They're gone.
But... Chaozii's with them.
Lavi, Krory, and Kanda.
[KIE]
Now what?
Something strange is
falling from the sky!
[TIEDOLL, BOOKMAN panting]
[TIEDOLL gasps]
What in the world
is happening?
[TIEDOLL] It looks like a...
glowing cube.
[chanting]
[MIRANDA]
He's saying something.
But what language
is he speaking?
[chanting continues]
The legendary Noah's Ark.
It finally appears.
And I can guess where the
missing Exorcists were taken.
[ALL screaming]
[thud]
Well... That certainly
was distressing.
[KANDA growls]
Uh...!
Could you do me a
favor and get off?
[LAVI groans]
Any idea what town this is?
Uh.
I know this place.
We're inside the Ark!
[CHAOZII]
Huh?
If you know so much,
tell me why we're here.
Like I have all the answers.
[KRORY] I don't think this
is the time to fight.
[LENALEE groaning]
[LAVI] Hey, Lenalee.
Did the fall hurt you?
[LERO groans]
[LAVI]
Check it out.
Looks like we landed on some
kind of pumpkin-headed toy.
[LERO] How dare you smush Lero,
damn Exorcists!
Guys! It can talk!
[ALLEN, KANDA] Huh? You're the
one responsible for this.
[KANDA] Start talkin' unless you
want us to carve you a new face.
[ALLEN]
The exit. Where is it?
[LERO] Uh. You see, the
thing is, there is no exit.
Lero!
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
After years of faithful service,
I'm afraid this Ark is no
longer in operational order.
Thank you for your work, Lero.
As for you, Exorcists, it's
time to begin your journey.
Welcome to the final voyage!
A one way trip aboard the Ark.
Destination, straight
to the afterlife!
Please watch your step.
As you can see certain areas
have already been transferred
to the new ship and are
starting to collapse.
Enough games! What's going on?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
So impatient.
The Ark is disintegrating
and will be absorbed into
the gulf between dimensions.
Or to put it into terms simple
enough for you to understand:
You have three hours.
And once time's up,
you'll cease to exist
and all traces of you will
vanish into nothingness!
Aren't you a lucky young girl!
Surrounded by so
many good friends
that decided to take this
trip alongside you!
And look on the bright side...
You won't be lonely since all
of them are accompanying you
to the great beyond.
You're despicable.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Oh. Far from it.
In fact, I'm so merciful
I'll do you a favor.
I'll see to it that no one
has to mourn your deaths
by exterminating all your
friends and loved ones!
[BOOKMAN]
Something's headed our way.
Things just keep getting
better and better.
Marie. Tell me what you hear.
Based on the sound,
we're looking at 20--
up to 30 enemies
approaching.
What I do know, is that
they're all giant Akuma.
We have completely lost
contact with the others.
What do you suggest?
This is a terrible situation.
[TIEDOLL]
Hm?
[BOOKMAN]
What is that, General?
Go. You know I won't
try to stop you.
So, General?
[TIEDOLL]
Very well.
It appears we have
no other choice.
There's gotta be
a house in the Ark
that leads to the outside world!
I used one of them
to get to Edo!
We've destroyed dozens and
we aren't getting anywhere.
[LERO]
Stupid humans, Lero!
The ship has stopped operating!
It's no longer connected to
the other dimensions, Lero!
There's no exit!
[LERO yelps]
[LENALEE gasps]
It's collapsing!
[LERO]
You'll never leave.
Seriously. There's
no way off this ship.
You guys are all going
to die here, Lero!
[TYKI]
Actually...
[gasps]
[TYKI]
...I can think of one way out.
[GIANT AKUMA roar]
[MIRANDA panting]
Miranda?
[BOOKMAN]
You're not hurt, are you?
Just a little faint.
Did something happen to Allen
and the others inside the Ark?
[MIRANDA]
Mm-hm.
[ALL gasping]
There's no way we can
fight off that many!
Step back!
[MARIE grunts]
[GIANT AKUMA C groans]
Activate Noel Organon.
[music plays]
Play "Melody of Sorrow"!
[GIANT AKUMA groan]
[GIANT AKUMA C groans]
[GIANT AKUMA D roars]
I call forth... Maker of Eden!
Activate!
You shall come to realize
the beauty of this world.
Art!
[GIANT AKUMA D roaring]
[TIEDOLL]
Art!
[GIANT AKUMA E groans]
[gasps]
[GIANT AKUMA E groaning]
More Akuma, eh?
They must be eager to taste
defeat.
[panting]
[BOOKMAN] Try to conserve
your strength, Miranda.
You're so tired from
healing the others,
you weren't able
to heal yourself.
The best thing for you is to
stay here with the crewmen
and minimize your exhaustion.
In addition to helping us,
you're sending your powers
to those inside the Ark.
It's understandable that
you're feeling weak.
I'm failing you.
You're not.
We can't afford to let anything
happen to you child,
or the wounds Allen and the
others sustained will return.
I can feel them.
Allen and everyone else
within the Ark.
Their injuries are still
inside my Innocence.
At the very least, we know
they're still alive.
And yet...
One thing troubles me.
I'm not using my full
recovery power right now,
which maintains everyone
at their optimal state.
The power I'm using only takes
away injuries from the past.
Which means any new damage
they sustain won't heal.
I should've pushed myself.
I should've used my full
recovery power.
[ALLEN gasps]
[TYKI]
There is one way out.
Remember me? [chuckles]
[ALLEN gasping]
Heh.
Uh. Yeah. But...
If you let me use
it as collateral,
I'll play some hands.
If I win, I get his stuff back.
Allen! Hold up!
You sure about this?
[TYKI laughs]
Deal.
[ALLEN]
I call!
[laughs]
[ALL]
A freakin' royal straight flush?
Gimme a break!
Ah! Screw this game!
Catch!
They're yours!
Consider it a token
of my thanks!
[ALL]
You're the nerdy glasses guy!
What? You seriously
call me that?
What the...? Why are you...?
How did you get in here?
It's kinda a long story.
[KANDA]
Hey.
[ALL gasping]
Careful. This guy's
oozing with bloodlust.
So. How about it, boy?
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[TYKI]
Tell me why you won't die.
[ALLEN groaning]
I had to endure a lot of
ridicule because of you.
Even from the Earl himself.
[ALLEN]
What? You're crazy!
Who are y--?
[TYKI]
Heh.
[ALL gasp]
[TYKI] Are you still
looking for a way out?
'Cause I might know of one.
[gasps]
[ALLEN grunts]
[TYKI chuckles]
[growls]
The Ark is no longer capable
of providing exits.
But perhaps, if we were to use
Road's power, we could make one.
That door just appeared
from out of the ground!
[gasps]
[LERO]
Lero? This door is familiar.
It belongs to Mistress Road!
Out of all the Noah,
Road's the only one
with the ability to move
between dimensions without
having to rely on the Ark.
So, how about we continue
our little game?
I'll wager the exit,
and you'll bet using the
only thing you have...
...your lives.
But this time,
there's no cheating.
Do we have a deal?
[ALLEN gasps]
[LERO] Tyki! What do you
think you're doing, Lero?
You know the Earl
never said you could!
[TYKI] Here's the key
that opens Road's door,
and the three doors
that lead to it.
And it can be yours.
Think it over.
But don't take too long.
After all, time's
not on your side.
[ALL grunt]
[LERO]
Tyki!
The tower fell on top him!
He must be completely flattened!
[KANDA grunts]
[TYKI] There's no game I enjoy
more than hunting Exorcists.
[LERO]
Lero...
[TYKI]
Only seems fair
I place the exit at the
highest point in the Ark.
If you make it there before
everything collapses,
you win your freedom.
[ALLEN] From what I hear,
Noah's are immortal.
In my book, that's
called cheating.
[TYKI laughs]
You heard wrong, boy.
I don't know how these
stories get started,
but let me set the
record straight...
...we're as human
as the rest of you.
We only appear immortal.
It's easy to confuse us with
gods when you're so weak.
[ALLEN growls]
[screams]
[ALL screaming]
[KANDA]
We have to get moving!
Head for more stable ground!
[LENALEE panting, screaming]
Someone help her!
Hold on tight!
We're getting out of here!
[ALL panting]
[LAVI]
So, what's the plan?
According to the Earl, this
place disappears in three hours.
If he's telling the truth,
all we're accomplishing
with running is delaying
the inevitable.
[LERO]
Actually, you have two hours.
Whichever way you
split it, we're doomed!
Lenalee and I have both
witnessed Road teleport before.
She can move between dimensions.
True...
[inaudible]
We shouldn't trust Tyki.
But using the door to escape
does seem feasible.
The way I see it,
there's two possibilities.
Road's door is probably a trap,
but on the other hand...
...it might be our only
way out of the Ark.
[sighs] We really don't
have any choice.
[KANDA grunts]
[GROUP]
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
Do we feel okay about this door?
Honestly, I don't think
it really matters.
[LENALEE, KRORY]
Mm.
[KANDA]
Hurry up already.
[gasps]
[LAVI] You know,
indecision is the reason
you lost rock, paper, scissors.
[ALL gasp]
We're in this together, right?
[LAVI] You bet.
[KRORY]
Indeed.
[LENALEE]
Yep.
[CHAOZII]
Definitely!
Um. Kanda.
I don't think so.
Of course.
Let's go.
What is this place?
[LAVI]
Wherever we are,
I don't think we've
left the Ark.
[KANDA gasps]
Uh. Something wrong?
[ALL gasp]
[ALLEN growls]
[KANDA]
Go on ahead.
Leave him to me.
You're sure?
This guy's been after
my General for awhile.
It's not our first encounter.
There's no way we're gonna leave
you here by yourself, Kanda.
[KANDA]
Don't get the wrong idea.
[BOTH gasp]
[KANDA]
The reason I'm staying
is not for your sakes.
I told you this thing's
after General Tiedoll.
[KANDA]
It's my duty to take him down.
[ALL gasping]
[ALLEN] The Noah Skinn
Bolic changes his form
and is able to wield powerful
lightning attacks.
Facing off against him is Kanda.
The swordsman stands silent.
Mugen held at the ready.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"The Skinn Bolic Room!"
Bring salvation to this
poor Akuma's soul.
[slurping]
--[MILLENNIUM EARL chuckles]
--[BOTH gasp]