Lenalee! Lenalee!
It's just like before.
You were there...
when I woke up.
Maybe you've forgotten it...
The day you came to The Order?
No... I remember.
Is Allen alright?
Yes, he's fine...
He's on assignment...
collecting Innocence with Kanda.
Oh...
Hey, you decided to wake up!
Thank goodness, do you
feel alright, Allen?
Oh, gosh, I'm so sorry, Lavi...
I'm sure I can...
You okay?!
Uh, yeah...
Grab my hand.
Thanks.
Idiot.
You feel so warm...!
Would you like me to
bring you a cool towel?
Uh, no... thanks.
It's alright, Allen, just relax.
You're pathetic.
You couldn't even take care
of one Akuma could you...?
We don't let them escape...
we finish them off.
Yeah, you don't
show any mercy, Yu,
to Akuma or to your teammates.
Where is Michael, the Finder?
How should I know?
He's not my responsibility...
Finders have to be able
to take care of themselves.
But he...
Michael!
Speak of the devil, we
were just talking about you!
Yeah, I saw the light
through the windows.
Well, we're glad you made it!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Did you see any
Akuma around the cabin?
No, I didn't.
So they went ahead...
I'm going out...
I want to find the Innocence
and collect it before they do.
Nice--I'll come back you up...
You planning to get lost again?
Watch it, Exorcist.
Don't worry, Father,
I'll be right beside you.
Do you even care about
your daughter's safety?
None of us should leave now...
It's too dark...
Then maybe you
should stay here, 'kay?
Seriously, just kick back
and take it easy...
Get some rest.
Okay.
In that case, I'll stand by
here, too, until I'm needed.
Take care...
We'll see you soon!
It's like we're going
on a field trip, huh?
Be quiet.
You know, you really
need to lighten up, Yu...
I said be quiet!
Ah, the Exorcists...!
Shall we attack?
Don't be a fool.
Why would we do such a
thing when we can use them
to find the Innocence and
then take it for ourselves?
Oh, brilliant--indeed,
that sure is a smart plan!
The source of the snowstorm
is probably from a material
called Innocence, not
the Leaf of Revival.
And even if you did obtain it,
you still wouldn't be able
to bring back your
son as he once was.
That's enough!
It's likely that Akuma are
outside waiting for us,
you and your daughter
should turn back now...
Please, sir, only
Exorcists can defeat Akuma.
Father...
Let's go to bed now...
We can leave in the morning.
But, Elda...
I'm sorry, Allen, we have to.
Jacob, Jacob!
No...
Don't come in!
Jacob!
Don't...!
Father, get them
away from here...
Go!
No!
Elda, is everything alright?
Where's my Father...?
Look, do you think...
I want you to wait
inside the cabin...
We'll track him down soon.
I'll come, too!
But you...
No!
I can't lose
another one, Allen...!
I don't want any more regrets--I
have to try to save him!
Elda...
If I hadn't stopped my father
from going in after Jacob,
then he wouldn't be suffering
like this, so it's my fault!
You have no idea
how much I regret
surviving the fire
without my brother.
Fine... I understand.
Timcanpy...!
We're counting on you!
Is this it?
I guess, let's go see!
Oh, and just how do
you propose we do that?
Well... let's look for
a break in the weather...
Wood... Circle!
Wood Stamp!
Spinning Disc...!
Of heaven and earth!
I almost forgot...
Lavi's Innocence
possesses the ability
to manipulate and
control nature.
Why don't we get inside
while we still can?
Whoa... Hey, are you okay?
The Leaf of...
I found it.
The Leaf of Revival...
I found it--it
really does exist!
I'll be able to bring
you back to us now, Jacob.
Oh my dear boy!
Oh, Jacob... Jacob!
Stop!
It's dangerous!
Mugen... Un-sheath!
Wood... Circle!
It's... no good!
We've got what
we came here for...
Let's go.
Please...
Give that to me...!
I need the Leaf of Revival
to bring back my son!
This is not the
Leaf of Revival...
It's called Innocence.
Give it to me!
No!
Innocence does
not have the power
to give your son back his life.
Accept it.
I'm sorry, but what
he says is true.
Do you finally believe us?
I don't quite understand why,
but this Innocence somehow
came to live in this tree
and made its leaves shine,
causing many people
to believe that this
was the Leaf of Revival.
That's why they came
here to pick its leaves...
If that had continued to happen,
the tree would've
eventually died...
So the Innocence caused
massive snowstorms
and hot winds to prevent
people from coming near it.
It was protecting itself,
however, I don't think that
it meant to hurt any one of us.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah.
Well, the weather cleared up!
Head's up.
Now hand that
Innocence over to us!
You'd better stand back.
They must not get
the Innocence--
this time there's no escape.
Let me take care of
the one on the left.
No one's stopping ya!
Big Hammer... Little Hammer...
Grow, Grow... Grow!
Take, that!
How could you both
be so pathetic?
Stop!!
Stop it!
I see. She absorbed the others
into herself to become stronger.
You know she may be
even tougher than you.
Now... you will give
the Innocence to me!
She's a lot stronger now!
Hey...!
What the hell are you doing?!
Give it to me...
I need that thing!
Let go of me!
Ready...!
Yu!
Damn you...
give me back my son!
You... fool!
Take this!
Dammit!
It's--
We made it!
Innocence... activate!
Firing!
Allen!
Nuisance!
Hey...!
Quickly, free my legs!
Hurry up!
Whoa, what about me?!
Alright everybody, here we go!
Right...!
You ready, Kanda?
Please...
Please give it to me.
I don't believe this.
I have to bring
him back to us...
my dear little boy...
I want it to be like before.
Just one more time.
I'm sorry...
It's all because I stopped you
from going in to save him.
No!
I had no idea my actions
would cause you to
suffer this much, Father.
And that's why I can't stop you
from doing anything now,
even if it's chasing after a
Leaf that I know doesn't exist.
Don't you think it's
time you started
paying attention to your
child that's still alive?
You're so intent on
pursuing your lost son
that Elda is being
hurt and neglected.
Do you even realize that
you're treating this girl
as though she's
the one who died,
no matter how much
she's done for you?
Please, don't worry about me...
I understand how sad you are.
Really, I'm fine and
I love you, Father.
Oh, Elda.
I'll go ahead and take this
Innocence back to The Order.
What... you don't want
to wait and go with us?
No. I think I've had
enough of this field trip.
I guess we should
head out, too.
Oh, right.
Should we make our
way home as well?
I'm sure your
mother's worried sick.
Figures...
I guess I'll have to
wait and do it myself.
Lero?
Lero!
Leroooo!
Give him back...
Without Lero around
everything is so boring.
Fine...
I don't care what you do...
I'm going after the
Innocence, so take him!
Oh, Lord Millennium told me
to tell you to
come back right now.
Why?
I don't know, Skin,
but I think we've
got some work to do.
Thank you so much...
for everything.
You're welcome.
We're planning
to stay one more day
and then go home to my Mother.
Before you go...
Yes?
Remember that it's not over,
you and your father
are still in danger.
Akuma are the result
of loss and tragedy.
They're used for dark purposes.
But how?!
Just be careful...
It's possible The Millennium
Earl might come for you.
If he offers to bring your
brother back from the dead,
promise me you won't listen.
We're not wishing
such things anymore...
I think we'll be too busy
loving the family members
who are still with
us here and now,
while both of us
look to the future.
I will not forget
to cherish these precious
lives ever again...
C'mere.
Oh, dad.
Goodbye!
I really hope the Millennium
Earl leaves Elda's family alone.
I'm reading your mind...
You know, you're an
open book, Allen...
It's true, if her brother were
to someday become an Akuma...
We'd have no choice but to
defeat him, because it's...
it's our gift and calling
as Exorcists, isn't it...?
We will always fight.
And protect those
that are in need.
So, what do you
think of Allen Walker?
I'm not sure yet...
but you know...
...somehow I don't imagine
his journey will ever be easy.
I mean, just look at him.
Let him be...
Kanda has gone missing while
on assignment in Rome...
We were dispatched to
rescue him and found
the legend of an immortal
swordsman waiting for us.
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"Millennium Swordsman."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul!