This "Edo Connection,"
what is it exactly?
[CROSS]
Just give the order.
I'll explain.
If you give the word,
it'll allow us to escape.
[ALLEN]
You know, Master,
you could've just said
that in the first place.
Did you hear that?
Yeah?
So play! What're
you waitin' for?
Let's get this over
with, short stack.
What did I tell you about
getting my name wrong?
Now's not the time, boys!
Ark, please cancel this
ship's connection to Edo.
[ALLEN] Do you hear me,
Ark? Open the gate.
The new destination will be...
[MIRANDA]
It's all my fault.
If only I had tried harder...
Look over there!
[BOOKMAN]
What is it?
[gasps]
Impossible!
[LAVI] Hey, everybody!
What did we miss?
[BOOKMAN]
Lavi?
[chuckles]
They found a way out!
What a relief! We really are
connected to the outside!
We're finally free!
[MIRANDA]
They're back.
All the time that
disappeared is returning!
Kanda survived too!
You're all so damn emotional.
[MARIE] Master Tiedoll!
Kanda's all right!
[TIEDOLL]
I know. I know.
Marie, do me a favor and ask him
if my new apprentice
is in one shape.
[KANDA]
You mean him?
[yelps]
Reporting.
Good to see you. I'm so
relieved you're all alive!
[OTHERS]
You can stop crying already!
Old man, aren't
you gonna say hi?
[grunts]
Well now, is that crying I hear?
[LAVI yelps]
I'm glad to see you too!
You idiot!
[LAVI]
Sorry.
[BOOKMAN] You're going to
give me a heart attack.
[WONG]
Director Bak!
No running in the halls.
What is it, Wong?
[WONG]
It's the Ark!
There's an entrance! A new
doorway has appeared!
[BAK]
Walker!
Oh, hey, Bak.
[BAK]
She's here.
[ALLEN]
We wanna contact headquarters.
Do you think we could
use your phone?
[BAK]
It's Lenalee!
Damn it! I got too worked up!
[WONG]
Director Bak!
Don't die on me!
Allen, who is that?
His name's Bak. He's the
Director of the Asian Branch.
If he's the one in charge,
how is this place
still standing?
Endure the pain and
survive for me!
[LO HUA]
I missed you so much, Allen!
Lo Hua! Hey, Li Kei, Shifu.
[LO HUA] You don't know
how glad I am you're okay!
Please don't start crying!
Wait, who is this?
She's obviously Allen's lover.
Hold up! What are
you implying exactly?
I think there's a mistake!
I doubt it.
[ALLEN] Hey! Where do
you think you're...?
Be honest.
On a scale of ten, eleven!
Sorry for the wait.
[LENALEE]
Stop, General! You can't leave!
Please let go of my face.
Don't disappear on us again!
[BAK screams]
[CROSS] How does one
say "no" to those eyes?
[LENALEE] I'm sick of
having to track him down!
[ALLEN] So that's why Lenalee
was assigned to the Cross Unit.
Komui's secret weapon.
He must've been
desperate to find him.
Can someone finally explain
to me who General Cross is?
[LO HUA squeals]
[LO HUA]
Did you hear that?
He called me Allen Walker's
woman! We're an item!
It's official!
At least they're happy.
[WONG]
Speak to me Bak!
Lenalee's purity. Her hair.
It's too much for me!
[WONG]
You have to find the strength
to pull yourself together!
[LAVI] I'm having real concerns
about the Asian Branch.
[STAFF gasping]
[ALL]
Welcome home!
[LENALEE]
Komui.
Big brother!
[STAFF cheering]
Welcome back, dear Lenalee.
I'm home.
It's time, Miranda.
We're ready for
whatever happens next!
Let go of me, Marie!
--Better safe than sorry.
--I know what's gonna happen!
Well, this is it.
Hope everyone's ready.
Now deactivating Time Record.
Get a stretcher!
[LENALEE gasps]
You've finally come to.
Miranda!
You shouldn't be pushing
yourself, Lenalee!
It's our job to take
care of the injured.
That includes you.
You helped bring
everyone home;
now it's our turn to help you.
The Black Order requires both
Exorcists and healers.
We take pride in our
work. Same as you.
[ALLEN]
I'm a wreck.
Look on the bright side,
at least you survived.
We made it.
You're right.
It feels good.
Good to finally be back home.
[KOMUI]
Welcome home.
[BAK humming]
Where do you think you're
going, my dear Director Bak?
[screams]
[KOMUI] And what a lovely
bouquet of flowers
you have there!
[BAK]
Oh! What? These?
[KOMUI]
I thought I was clear.
Lenalee is not to have
visitors in her condition.
[KOMUI] I'll pass along
this pathetic arrangement!
Isn't the Asian Branch
having a difficult time
after the Akuma's attack?
You should head back since
you don't have a reason
to be here anymore.
Think again.
[BAK] The only thing pathetic
was your attempt to stop me!
[KOMUI'S DOLL] Never. No matter
what. Danger. Do not enter.
Never. No matter what...
[BAK]
Then I'll just have to go over!
[KOMUI'S DOLL] Never. No matter
what. Danger. Do not enter.
You think you can stand
in the way of my love
with such petty obstacles?
[KOMUI'S DOLL] Never. No matter
what. Danger. Do not enter.
Never. No matter what.
Danger. Do not enter.
[BAK]
Komui!
The warnings were in place
for your own safety.
[KOMUI'S DOLL]
Never. No matter what...
So sorry, Bak. Next time.
[REEVER]
Uhh...
It's breathtaking.
You'll agree, the Ark is an
amazing feat in engineering.
Quite different from how
the books describe it.
[WONG] Careful not to
get too close, sir.
[REEVER]
If I could echo that warning.
Let's say one were to
enter through the gate
in a manner like so...
[REEVER]
Um, Director?
[BAK] ...they'd be instantly
transported inside the Ark.
Excuse me.
[BAK] And were you
to go through here...
...you'd be transported to a
completely different place.
A "space time warp" as they call
it in science fiction novels.
[LI KEI]
Hey, Chief! No fair!
[STAFF A] How come you
get to go in by yourself?
We wanna explore the Ark, too!
I just want to
visit Headquarters!
[BAK] Remarkable
teleporting abilities.
Tell me, Section Leader Reever,
is the Ark currently situated
over the Black Order in Europe?
[REEVER]
Yeah...
[BAK] In addition,
I couldn't help but notice
besides its teleporting ability,
the Ark also has
several internal spaces
I like to call rooms.
Rooms where the Exorcists
fought the Noah,
the one for the Akuma factory,
and the mysterious piano.
It's difficult to believe
science like this has existed
for several thousand years.
And just who exactly
is the Millennium Earl?
Section Leader, why is
that guy even in here?
The Chief said no one
should enter the Ark,
so technically we
shouldn't be here either.
Not to worry gentlemen,
for I am a brilliant scientist.
My opinion gives us
permission to be here.
But you're only a
branch chief, right?
[REEVER]
Quiet, Johnny! Shh!
[KOMUI wailing]
You're crying way too
much, big brother.
[KOMUI] But it's gone!
Your beautiful hair!
Correction! The world's
most beautiful hair!
Get a grip on yourself, Komui!
[KOMUI]
But! But! But I can't help it!
If you can't control yourself,
you'll have to leave!
Not only are you being too loud,
but you're dirtying
the bed sheets, Chief!
What's so filthy about
these tears of grief?
It's your face!
You cut right to
the bone, head nurse.
Don't you think it's time for
you to head back to your office?
You've got a lot of
work to do, right?
[KOMUI]
I guess.
When I get better, I'll make
a strong pot of coffee for you.
Yeah.
Go to sleep...
[KOMUI]
Before I leave,
I made you this pillow that
plays a soothing lullaby.
My sweet, Lenalee...
That's not going near her.
[KOMUI]
But--! Uh, good night, Lenalee!
[chuckles]
[LENALEE]
Sorry about the racket.
You don't get it, Lenalee.
[LENALEE]
Huh? What's there to get?
The chief was just excited
to see you again.
He looked so happy.
[stomach growling]
[LAVI] Don't just stand there,
nurse! Do something!
I can't sleep with Krory's
stomach going crazy!
[NURSE A]
I don't know what to do.
I'd like to feed him, but I
can't until he wakes up first.
Sorry, Lavi.
Think that's rough?
I'm right beside him and have
a keen sense of hearing.
Hey, Kanda. Are you planning
some kind of escape?
How do they expect
me to get any sleep?
I'm going back to my room!
You can't go.
We haven't gotten permission
to leave the infirmary.
[KANDA]
Watch me.
[TIEDOLL] Yu Kanda. You should
listen to Marie for a change.
Step aside, General.
I just came by to see how
my precious sons were healing.
Speaking of which, what are you
doing out of bed in your state?
We're not your sons, Tiedoll.
And I would appreciate
it if in the future,
you would refrain from
addressing me as such.
I view all my apprentices
as though they were children.
Stop acting so embarrassed
and think of me like a father
doting on a sick child.
Just give up, Kanda.
That's the kind of
man our master is.
Kind? Smothering?
You represent everything
I despise in humans!
[NURSE A]
Stop! No violence in the ward!
[MARIE]
Settle down, Kanda!
So that guy is gonna be
your new master, Chaozii?
Yeah.
Well, he's certainly different.
Anyway, now that things
have settled down,
what're you guys planning next?
We're talking to
the Order to see
if they'll let us be Finders.
Really? That's great!
You didn't think we were gonna
leave you here alone, did ya?
By the way, have you
seen your hair?
Major bedhead.
[CHAOZII, MAOSA, KIE laughing]
Hey, Allen. You wanna
stop by the cafeteria?
You alive over there?
Allen?
Hello?
[LAVI]
It figures.
[TUP] Delicious as always.
You're somethin', Jerry.
[JOHNNY]
Allen!
[ALLEN]
Hm?
Hi, Johnny!
I know this is a little late,
but I wanted to thank you.
Huh? What're you talkin' about?
Regarding Suman, I heard things.
Like how you tried to save
him right to very end.
[ALLEN]
I tried, but I wasn't able to.
Forgive me.
[JOHNNY] There's nothing
to forgive. You tried.
Thank you!
Excuse me! I have to
get back to work!
Poor Johnny. He and Suman
used to be really good pals.
That's right. They would
play chess together.
[TUP] When he first
heard Suman had died,
he was inconsolable and fell
into a heavy depression.
We know Suman couldn't be saved.
But thank you for trying.
This is a lullaby,
isn't it, Timcanpy?
Strange.
When I read the poem,
in my head, it instantly
became a song.
Sometimes, it feels like there's
someone else up there with me.
Inside my head.
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN]
I lost my appetite.
[ALLEN] This path, is it the
road I've chosen to walk down?
For the rest of my life?
Is it even my decision?
Or did someone choose it for me?
That can't be true. Right, Tim?
How could it be?
Those symbols on the
musical score...
...they were letters Mana
and I invented together
a long time ago.
I'd forgotten about them.
Those symbols only
Mana and I could read.
A secret language we created.
[LULU BELL] Well, Master,
they actually did it.
The download was incomplete
and we lost up to
80% of the factory.
This must have been Cross
Marian's ultimate goal.
[MILLENNIUM EARL] We can't just
pop another one of these out!
It takes tremendous
amounts of resources!
At a time when we
desperately needed
to manufacture more Akuma.
What a setback.
[MILLENNIUM EARL] The Exorcists
stole the Ark from us.
They gained control when there
shouldn't have even been
a piano aboard!
And I know how.
It seems the Fourteenth's
curse is alive and well
on the Ark after all this time.
What is this feeling? Anger?
Earl? You okay, lero?
[MILLENNIUM EARL] The Exorcists
and the Fourteenth.
So they think they
can join forces
and sabotage the tree
of Noah, do they?
Filthy, rotten sheep!
I'll lead them all
to the slaughter!
[ALLEN]
Director Malcolm C. Rouvelier,
a Special Inspector
from the Central Agency,
holds an advisory
council meeting.
The subject, my Master.
What shocking revelation
is he about to unearth?
On the next D.Gray-man:
"Lamb and Dog."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
Tim doesn't need to eat,
so why is he going to
town on those dumplings?
I guess he's watched my
eating habits for so long,
that he's trying to mimic them.
[ALLEN yelps]
Not cool