Mana...
Do you remember the last time I
couldn't see out of my left eye?
I decided that even if
I lost that ability forever,
I'd still grow up strong and
train to join the Black Order...
Just like an exorcist...
I will be prepared...
Mana!
Now Allen...
you must go deeper...
...into the realm of
black... and white.
Thanks Mana.
Your eye is finally healed.
That's right...
I take back what
I said before...
I do have reason to fight now.
What a shame...
I guess you figured
me out... huh?
This bite?
It's probably gonna scar...
Thanks for pointing that out.
And now my outfit
is ripped to shreds.
That's your fault
since you transformed
into the Akuma I saw last night.
I told you not to set
foot in this castle...
But like a fool
you defied me anyway.
What are you waiting for?
Are you going to
transform or not...?
Don't you want to be in
your true Akuma appearance?
As far as I'm concerned
this is my true form...
And if it were up to me I'd
look like a human forever.
My Akuma form is...
hideous and gross!
I agree with you.
Now... I've got a headache;
let's call a truce and
go our separate ways.
Can't do that.
Then you're a fool.
You are such a cute
little thing... Exorcist...
So cute I think I will...
EAT YOU!!!
I don't think so.
This time when I hit
you, you stay down!
That's not good!
Uhh...
What's wrong?
Ah man.
Hey, Krory!
Are you okay?!
No... Not now...!
I need more power... more blood!
If only...
I had taken more from Eliade.
No Arystar...!
If you had sucked
any more of her blood,
you'd have killed
the love of your life!
Eliade!!
He must be having
a nervous breakdown...
Well... Not my problem.
I'm not here to hold his hand,
so lets take this
chance to pounce!
No hard feelings, Krory.
Innocence...
Level Two Release!
Stamp!
Fire circle!
Hellfire... Devouring...
Fire Stamp!
Don't worry, Krory...
That flame level wasn't lethal.
Thank you.
Hey, Allen.
You seem to be in
a bit of a hurry.
Appreciate the help, Lavi...
I think you may have
just saved my life.
Don't sweat it.
Arystar!
Convert!
Arystar, wake up!
Huh?
Wait... I think
I'm seeing things.
Allen...
Is that gorgeous
woman an... Akuma?
What?
Yeah...
I can see it...
There's a human soul
standing right beside her.
No way!
So you... you can
see it too... Lavi?
Allen...
I'm afraid... I can...
Come back... Come back to me!
Please honey...
Please come back!
I'm caught...
They've got me...
There is no escape...
I can't even breathe...
It's this woman's fault.
Welcome, young one.
Your fate now belongs to me.
Now, I order you
to kill this woman
and wear her body as your own.
What? You never
said I had to die!
No choice...
I have no choice...
Can't disobey...
Kill her...
Now!
This woman's words pulled
me back from the grave...
Her body became my own...
She certainly had a
figure worth admiring.
After transforming
into an Akuma,
I became a prolific killer...
...and it wasn't too
long before I evolved.
From then on,
I gained a sense of self,
and took interest
in other things...
Such as shopping, cosmetics,
dancing, parties, and
other extravagances...
I was now considered
attractive and desirable...
Men began to take notice,
throwing their
flirtatious advances
toward me at every turn.
Their looks were intoxicating.
But at the core
I was still an Akuma.
Killing became more of
an instinct then an act...
All of those men
who wished to be mine
became my victims
quite easily...
However, the effects
of killing made me ugly.
No longer was
I pretty... or desired...
It was then that I noticed,
that I could never truly
be a human being again...
I thought to myself...
"There's something
I want to try... just once...
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself
if I didn't at
least attempt it."
But it's an impossibility...
Because we are machines...
Programmed to slaughter humans.
It's me, Eliade.
I've been observing your skill
at deceiving and killing humans
and I must say it's
quite impressive...
Thank you, Lord.
Would he expect any less of me?
After all, he was responsible
for programming me
to behave that way...
You have an assignment...
There's a man that goes
by the name of Arystar Krory
who I'm suspicious of, and
I'd like you to investigate him.
Arystar... Krory?
There's a high probability
that he's been in contact
with the Exorcist General
Cross, making him a threat...
You will have an
unlimited supply
of Level One Akuma at
your disposal, so use them.
Even if there's
nothing on Krory,
kill him anyway just
to be on the safe side.
Yes, Lord.
Lord Millennium, let's play!
Ahhh, Road...
I've been looking
for you everywhere!
My Lero's gone.
You didn't happen to
steal it again did ya?
Who cares?
Even if I did, you'd
still forgive me, right?
No no no no no!
You have it all
wrong, you little pest!
Stop being a big baby!
You'll get him back.
I need Lero at a
moment's notice...
The Earl never
treats me like that.
No matter how pretty I am,
I could never speak
with him so playfully...
He's simply not interested
in me like that...
Why...? Because I'm
just another Akuma,
an underling that exists
only to do his bidding.
That still doesn't stop me
from dressing nicely
and wearing makeup...
I want to be pretty...
It feels good.
I only wish to be desired...
Like a human...
I just want to be real woman.
Would you shut up...?!
I just need to fix my makeup...
I can't concentrate
if I don't look good!
We don't have time for breaks.
The Earl won't be pleased...
Just go on without me.
I'll catch up with you later.
Why can't they keep their
opinions to themselves...?
This is why I can't stand
dealing with Level One Akuma.
I will continue on my killing
spree, there's no denying that.
And even though the path I'm on
is not what
I would prefer to do,
I'll evolve more and more
with each murder I commit...
But what will happen when
my evolution is complete?
I like human men...
because they like me...
They give me attention and
I feel like a real woman,
like I'm alive.
But I also dislike human men,
because they break so easily...
They tend to die at the
slightest touch from an Akuma.
If they knew what
I really was...
They would look away in disgust.
Human men are so...
Why can't I move?
I'm an Akuma, I should
be overpowering him!
Those fangs...
They're so sharp...
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm going to die...
this is it...
...bitten by this stranger...
This man... has destroyed me.
I'm still alive.
I can't believe what I just did!
I attacked this girl!
I was sucking her blood!
What is wrong with me...?
I'm a monster!
You're still alive?
You had a chance to kill me.
Why didn't you?
I... I stopped once
I realized what I was doing...
I'm... just so...
weak, Eliade...
I'm sorry... Please...
Please forgive me!
The sight of those fangs...
made my skin crawl.
Despite how
dangerous they were...
I was oddly...
attracted to them...
...I craved more.
I found you!
What?
It's my turn this time.
That is how Arystar
Krory and I first met.
Our relationship is
anything but normal.
Arystar is a human, whose
body is the host for Innocence.
So naturally, he and
I are sworn enemies,
though in reality
we are far from it.
He is unique due to his
superhuman abilities achieved
when drinking blood from Akumas.
But the Innocence
coursing inside him
makes his thirst for
blood unquenchable.
Since the day we met,
he's restrained himself
from drinking my blood because
he doesn't want to kill me...
It's taken all of his
strength to do so.
And whenever the urge
to drink overwhelmed him,
he would attack my fellow Akuma,
who had infiltrated
the village below...
He would do that for my sake.
I didn't care who he attacked...
I was happy as long
as we could be together
in this castle...
for the rest of time.
Arystar, can you
hear me?! Arystar!
Hello Eliade.
How are you feeling my darling?
But... wait... Eliade, look...
Do you see that thing?
Huh?
It's right... above you...
It looks like it's
coming out of your body.
What is it?
That's the soul of the Akuma
who's holding the
body against its will
so it can use it
as a power source...
Does that sound about right?
This is nuts...
I can... see it...
with my own eyes.
Ya know, Allen...
It must have something
to do with yours'.
My left eye has become...
more powerful...
Could Mana's curse have
increased my powers this much?
I don't understand how,
but other people are able to see
what only I could see before...
Which means...
Krory...! Do you
see the apparition
that is coming out
of your friend's body?
That is the soul of an Akuma...
Eliade is an Akuma!
She's an enemy to
both you and us!
Is that true, Eliade...?
Be honest...
Have you been deceiving me?
Are you an Akuma?
I...
I don't know what to say.
This blood...
Is it not... human blood?
I really wish that it didn't
have to come to this...
Oh no...
I was going to keep
you alive and use you,
but there's no
point to that now...
I will never allow you
to become an Exorcist...
That's why I have to kill you!
Not good...!
Fang boy can't defend himself
because he fought me earlier!
Fang boy?
Who is that?
Him...! Krory...
Flowers...?!
I thought we already got
rid of all these, Lavi!
Ah, looks like we need to
try a little harder, buddy...
There's too many of them!!
I don't care how pretty you
are or how good you smell,
I now officially hate flowers!
It looks like your
grandfather's precious flowers
have worked up an appetite...!
When I'm finished with you,
shall I feed your
body to them as well?
I loved you, Eliade.
I've loved you since the
moment I laid eyes on you...
But if I'm your enemy then,
why didn't you kill me
that day in the forest...
Rather than string
me along like this?
Like I said before,
I used you...
I needed you for something
I've been wanting to
do for a long time...
That's the only reason you're
still alive to this day.
Fine then...
I guess you've
made your choice...
Akuma.
I've a confession...
Eliade... I now yearn
for nothing more
than you drawing your
last dying breath...
So... We feel the
same way for each other.
We do.
Their feelings for each
other have reached
a boiling point as the fight
continues to rage on...
Once lovers, they are now
in a battle to the death.
Next time on D. Gray-man:
"The Vampire Whom I Loved."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.