And the one question
I want answered
is whether or not Allen Walker
is working for the enemy.
Whose side is he on?
Are you doubting one of our own?
[ROUVELIER]
Anyone is capable of duplicitous
and heretical machinations,
regardless of their
ranking as an Exorcist.
Go on, Director.
Investigate all you want.
Excuse me, General?
As far as Allen goes,
do whatever you feel
is appropriate.
What the hell are you saying,
Cross? Don't do this!
Very well then,
General Cross Marian.
Pleased to meet you.
Director Rouvelier has assigned
me to your guard detail.
I'm Howard Link, an
Inspector for the Order.
[LAVI]
Hm?
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[LENALEE]
Hm?
As a small gesture of
good will between us,
I baked you a pumpkin pie.
I do hope you like it.
[gasps]
Thanks! Good will accepted!
[LINK]
Glad to hear it.
Wait, you don't even
know who this guy is!
Did you even hear him
say he's your guard?
[LENALEE]
Tell me where my brother is!
[REEVER]
Uh. Lenalee! Wait!
[LENALEE]
Komui!
What's going on? Why does
Allen have a guard detail?
Not a good time!
[ROUVELIER]
Oh?
How nice to see you, Lenalee.
How do your legs feel?
Any improvement?
I didn't know...
you were here.
[ROUVELIER] Oh, Lenalee.
What're we going to do with you?
There's no running away
from the Order, child,
so please stop trying.
[ROUVELIER]
Now. You come to me.
Come.
It appears as though I'll be
here for an extended visit.
I'll also need to study your
Innocence at some point soon,
so please do cooperate.
[REEVER]
Dammit. I wasn't fast enough.
[ROUVELIER]
Oh. One other thing.
Here, would you care to try
my latest confectionery
creation before you go?
[KOMUI]
Whoa, that looks delicious!
Can I please try a little taste?
Yeah, the Director's cakes
are out of this world!
[KOMUI laughing]
[KOMUI]
Off with you now, Lenalee.
You need to run along
for your check up!
It is time for that!
Well, come on, Lenalee,
I'll walk you down!
[KOMUI laughs nervously]
[KOMUI]
Thanks, Reever! Wow, what a guy!
[KOMUI laughs nervously]
[REEVER]
Sorry about that. You okay?
[REEVER] Crap, I should've
had a guard on the door.
I didn't even think
about the experience
she had with him as a kid.
Ah, jeez, I'm such an idiot.
Section Leader Reever.
Why? Why do they have
a guard on Allen?
And what is Rouvelier
even doing here?
[ROUVELIER]
It's rather apparent Lenalee
still hasn't forgiven me,
even after all these years.
I could see it in her
eyes quite clearly.
[KOMUI] Let's return to the
matter at hand, Director.
So why are you guarding me?
Can you tell me that much?
It was the decision
of Director Rouvelier.
However, there is
the possibility
your surveillance
could be lifted,
depending on your answers
to this questionnaire.
I have plenty of questions
to ask you as well,
but I'll save them
for the library.
Why couldn't we do all
this in the cafeteria?
I'm capable of answering
questions in there.
I barely got to touch my food.
It was far too noisy in there
for us to properly concentrate.
That is not the
library, Mr. Walker!
Really? Guess I got
turned around.
[CROSS] Are you serious?
Who bought this cheap booze?
Oh, great.
[CROSS] They really expect
me to drink this swill?
You bastards are supposed
to be my caretakers!
So take care of me and go buy
me some decent booze right now!
[AGENT A] The Director gave
us very strict orders
to keep you on a tight budget.
Could you bother
to explain to me
why you need me here
to drink with you?
'Cause there's nothin'
better than drinkin'
with a beautiful
woman, that's why.
Four years since I've seen you,
and you are just as gorgeous
as the first time I saw you.
And you're just as much of
a hopeless deviant, as ever.
[CROSS yelps]
If it isn't my dumb pupil.
What's the big idea?
That's exactly what
I wanted to ask you,
but I can see the only idea
in your head was to get drunk.
All right, Allen, wha'dya want?
[ALLEN] Did you really
just ask me what I want?
Okay, take it easy.
Is this about the sheet music?
I'm sorry about this, Allen.
[LINK]
You and General Cross Marian
are forbidden to
speak, understand?
What? Why not? What's the deal?
Hang on! Hey, Master!
What is this? Why
can't I talk to him?
It's a direct command
of the Order.
[ALLEN]
The Order?
I don't get it, why do they
wanna keep us apart?
I was waiting to tell you
this in the library,
but since you're
making a scene...
You're under suspicion for your
involvement with the Fourteenth.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Wait. The Fourteenth?
Well, it looks as though
that name rang a bell.
No, um. Not at all.
Very well, then. Follow me.
I'll provide you
with the details.
We'll see if I can't
jog your memory.
[LINK]
The Fourteenth was a Noah
who happened to be
murdered by his own clan.
His real name is unknown to us.
All of our historical
records state
that there were originally
only thirteen Noah
that lived throughout
the past few millennia.
He was mysteriously born
sometime in the recent past.
Due to these reasons, we only
know him as the Fourteenth.
Any of this starting to
sound familiar to you yet?
[ROUVELIER] As recorded
in the document you hold,
we know the Fourteenth
was killed by his own.
Although,
there is a scattered group that
have dedicated themselves
to his posthumous cause.
Is that so?
[ROUVELIER] We don't know the
exact number of these adherents.
But we do know that
General Marian Cross
ranks as one of them.
That can't be true.
[ROUVELIER]
Oh, it is.
Furthermore, I believe that he
took Allen Walker as his protégé
because he knew that
Walker's the Player.
Your facts are starting to
sound like speculation to me.
[ROUVELIER] Please, Chief,
can you honestly tell me
that you don't find
this information
the least bit worrisome?
A mysterious,
previously unknown Noah,
and a conclave including
one of our own generals
plotting to fulfill
his last wish,
and none of this troubles you?
[ALLEN]
I'll tell you this now.
I'm not plotting anything.
And I've never heard of
the Fourteenth before,
so quit trying to remind me.
[LINK] Oh, sure, you
don't know anything.
Because nobody ever denies
their own culpability.
[thunder rumbles]
Now listen up.
You can deny your involvement
with the Fourteenth
as much as you want,
but your actions have already
confirmed your connection.
What other explanation is
there for how you knew
the melody to operate the Ark?
And how else could you
know how to read this?
That... But how?
Well, now that's
a look of surprise.
You didn't tell Chief Komui
about this sheet music, did you?
Do I have proof to
back up these claims?
Come now. Of course I do.
In fact, living,
breathing proof at that.
The Order happens to have one
of the Fourteenth's adherents
in our custody as we speak.
He's quite the infirm
and frail old man.
After devoting so much of
his life to the Fourteenth,
he came to fear that
the Earl would kill him.
So he came to us for protection.
And believe me, we have
learned a great deal from him.
The symbols on here,
our scholars pored over them.
They don't belong to any
known people or culture.
And despite this fact,
you're capable of reading them.
[ALLEN]
Because...
That's only because they're...
the letters I created with Mana.
Did somebody teach you how
to decipher these symbols?
Who taught you?
[ALLEN]
But... I can't.
[LINK] Are these symbols
some kind of covert code
created by the Fourteenth?
[ALLEN]
I can't tell them.
Mana was just a
travelling clown.
I was an orphan and he
took me in and raised me.
And that's all there is to it.
[LINK]
Speak up, Walker. Am I wrong?
It's you. Why are you here?
What?
[ALLEN]
There! Behind me! In the window!
I don't see anything other
than our reflections.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
You don't see it.
You're resorting to theatrics
now that you're cornered?
How childish can you get?
[ALLEN] It's not an act.
I think I'm losing my mind.
Mana, you and I, we were
just an orphan and a clown.
That's what I always believed.
But if that's not so... If we
were more, then what were we?
Is it just me, or is the
atmosphere kind of tense today?
Yeah, everyone's on edge
because of Walker and Cross.
Rumors are spreading
like wildfire.
What kind of rumors?
[MEMBER A] I heard
the Noah brainwashed them
and sent them in
to infiltrate us.
[MEMBER B]
Yeah.
That's why the Central
Agency's snooping around.
[BAK]
That's just ludicrous!
Leave them be.
Trying to repudiate gossip
only strengthens it.
Trust me, it'll blow
over soon enough.
[NANSEN]
You really think so?
We are in the middle
of a war, after all.
It's life and death,
and people are desperate,
frantic, and scared.
If a rift develops between us,
it could likely be disastrous.
Allen Walker is a good guy!
He's not working with
the Noah, he's with us!
Allen's my friend.
He's a good guy.
Listen, I know you care
about your friends,
but you can't let it
get to you so much
'cause some morons are
talkin' bad about them.
Yeah, people are just
freaking out right now.
They'll snap out of it once
they start to calm down.
And hey, we're with you, man,
we know that Allen's a good guy.
[JOHNNY]
Thanks, guys. Really.
Hey, good mornin'.
Oh, hey, good morning, Lavi.
Oh, wow. You got some
heavy bags under your eyes.
Must be tough to sleep with
a mole spying on you all night.
What? You're a very
rude young man.
[ALLEN] Jeez, Link, don't let
him get under your skin.
Lavi's practically still a kid.
He just likes giving
people nicknames.
Just ignore him and he'll get
bored and leave you alone.
[LAVI chuckles]
[LAVI]
Hey. A kid?
You do know that I'm older
than you, right, Allen?
[ALLEN] Doesn't make you
any more mature, though.
I'm surprised.
I thought you'd be more upset
about everything goin' on,
but you seem pretty chipper.
[ALLEN]
Well, you know how it is.
Sure, maybe I'm seeing
things that aren't there,
but what can I do about it?
Everything is out of
my control, right?
There's not much
point in getting upset
over something that's
out of your hands.
[ALLEN] What is this? They've
set up a restricted area?
[LAVI]
Hm? What's goin' on?
Oh, good morning, everybody.
We finally got this thing
set up and ready to study.
The factory?
Wait a sec, did you guys
move that here from the Ark?
[REEVER] Yep. We couldn't
research it in there.
Yeah, sure, that's great.
Now when are you gonna get
around to fixing my hammer?
[REEVER] Look, it's on the list
of things to do, I promise.
But this is the
priority right now.
You guys realize
how huge this is?
It's bound to provide us
with invaluable information
about the Akuma.
Once we crack
all of its secrets,
it might give us
some kind of idea
of how we can finally win
this war against the Earl.
This find, it's the first true
beacon of hope for us.
Hope, huh?
What do you want?
Nothing.
I just thought it might be nice
to sit and meditate with you
for a change of
pace, that's all.
Because of Rouvelier?
You always come running to me.
He rears his head, and you
sprint in my direction.
I just don't like worrying the
others, but you don't worry.
Or if you do, you
never really show it.
And I like that you
don't ask questions.
But... I guess I'm just running.
I know I should face him.
I don't understand why I'm like
this! I hate feeling this way!
I've gotta be
stronger than this!
But I'm not... I'm just...
[sighs]
Lenalee.
You're one of the
strongest people I know.
[LENALEE]
Hm?
You mean that?
Just shut up and meditate now.
[LENALEE]
Huh?
[GOLEM A] Lenalee Lee. Please
come to Hevlaska's chamber.
Director Rouvelier and
Chief Komui await you.
[HEVLASKA]
Her synchronization rate
has dropped to
below ten percent.
It's fallen that low?
[HEVLASKA]
Her Innocence.
It's best to return it
to me at this time.
I'll restore it
to original form.
You're okay? You're
not in any pain?
I'm fine.
[ROUVELIER]
So what does this mean?
Is she incapable of
synchronizing now?
[HEVLASKA]
No, that's not the case.
Although, much as we
already witnessed
with Allen Walker's
left arm, the Innocence,
it has begun to develop
unprecedented properties.
I sense that it's begun to
develop a will of its own.
Just as the Akuma grow more
powerful by feeding on sorrow,
the Innocence has
begun to react
to the emotions of
the Accommodator.
As if...
[gasps] It's evolving?
Are you saying the Innocence
has begun to evolve?
[KOMUI]
Is that possible?
Perhaps it is.
But the stronger it grows,
the more it demands of its host.
Like a Parasite Type.
[LENALEE]
Huh?
Parasite Types are uncommon.
There are fewer of them
than Equipment Types
due to the strain.
Such a powerful, distilled form
of Innocence... is corrosive.
The constant surge
of energy required
feeds off of the
vitality of the host.
And such a ceaseless
assault on the body
shortens the lifespan
of the Accommodator.
[LENALEE]
What? Did she just...?
Komui. Is that true?
[ROUVELIER] Her Innocence is
becoming a Parasite Type?
[HEVLASKA]
I'm not sure yet.
But the next time
she synchronizes,
I suggest that she is prepared.
[LINK]
Walker!
Yeah?
Are you trying to give
yourself a heart attack?
You're 15 years old
and growing,
you need to eat some vegetables.
Yeah, sure, you're one to talk,
the only thing you eat is cake.
I'm 19, I can eat
whatever I want.
[ALLEN] What?
And how does that matter?
[LINK]
Because I'm an adult.
Just another peaceful,
lovely morning.
[JOHNNY] All right! I'm ready
for another hard day of work!
Let's get to it!
Johnny! C'mon, you're late!
Hurry up and bring
that box over here!
[JOHNNY]
Right! Sorry!
He's certainly in a
better mood today.
Guess so.
[BAK]
Wow, there it is.
All right. We're ready to work,
what've you got for us to do?
C'mon, guys.
[JOHNNY]
Whoa, hey, you can't come in!
You're not with
the Science Section!
[BAK] So what? I'm still
a damn great scientist!
[RENI] Yeah, you don't
have to be so rude.
You guys are
understaffed, right?
Well, we're here to help!
Oh, this is the
last thing I need.
Look, I'm sorry. I'm
not tryin' to be rude.
I'm just tryin' to
do my job, alright?
Sure, and what
important work it is.
[JOHNNY]
Exactly!
Uh.
What?
See. I've got a job to do.
What the hell?
Now then, let's get to work.
[ALLEN] Lulu Bell of the Noah
Clan suddenly appears in the lab
with a horde of Akuma.
Her ambush takes
everyone by surprise,
and no one knows
how to counter attack,
leaving the Order on
the verge of annihilation.
On the next D.Gray-Man:
"Attack on Headquarters."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
Yeehaw!
Hey, sorry, but who
are you again?
My name is Howard Link.
Why do you keep hovering
over me like that?
I'm keeping an eye on you.
But why?
Because you always
show up late to school,
you run in the hallway,
and you also bring snacks and
a Golem into the classroom,
that's why!
Really? Those are your reasons?
[ROUVELIER]
Heh-heh.