The storm is getting worse.
It'll be alright.
Do you think it's
safe to go out?
You know you're free to
stay behind until I get back.
Father, I'm going
to come with you...
If I stayed here
I'd only worry...
I just wish we knew where
to look for it... that's all.
This would be a helluva
lot more enjoyable for me
if all this yucky snow was
turned into sweet,
sweet ice cream.
Once we safely
collect the Innocence,
I'm sure the Earl will be happy
to make some for you, lero.
I thought the only thing
Lord Millennium could
make was Akuma.
I'd like cream stew,
pot stickers,
omelet with mushrooms,
green pepper steak,
fried rice, and a Caesar salad.
Mmm?
And ten cream puffs
and red bean paste
pancakes for dessert.
O-kay... and these
are large portions?
Uh-huh!
It's so fun to cook for you.
That was fantastic!
Whoa... you have
quite the appetite, huh?
Parasite Type
Exorcists need fuel
because they tend to
expend a lot of energy.
Yeah, they sure do.
Allen...
Yes?
New mission.
Huh?
Report to Chief Komui.
Sorry I'm late...
How do you like cold
weather...? How bout heat?
I'd say I'm fine with either.
Really...?!
Then you'll be perfect
for this next assignment.
We've learned of a village
experiencing abnormal
weather conditions...
It's snowing one minute,
while the next brings
blazing hot winds...
That's strange...
What's the cause?
We believe Innocence
is the most likely source
for such a phenomenon.
You and Kanda
are to retrieve it...
As a team of course.
Yes sir, understood.
Looking forward to it.
Didn't you know...?
We're taggin' along.
How annoying.
Oh now, don't say that.
We can all work together, Yu.
Do not call me that!
You know, since
I'm an Exorcist too,
I'll be able to help pitch in
and fight when we run into
Akuma... Isn't that right?
I'm sure we'll be glad
to have your help.
Lavi...
This is the perfect
chance for us
to confirm with our own eyes
if this is Hevlaska's
Destroyer of Time.
Yeah.
And that's when I decided
to go to China, and let me--
Hey, are you listening?!
I can't get any rest...
I don't know which
is more exhausting,
working with Kanda or
listening to these stories.
So there I was,
really hitting it off
with this beautiful Chinese girl
in an amazing silk dress...
It was like a dream!
Well, you wouldn't
believe it but then another,
even more beautiful girl
came in and...
Hey...
Did you fall asleep...?!
How rude.
This is gonna look so good...
Oh, you awake...?
That Allen fell asleep, too...
Ha... Yeah and something
seems to have happened
to his face so maybe you
should take a look see.
Heeeyyyy, you don't have
to get so worked up, Yu!
Thank you for coming...
I'm your Finder.
The name's Michael.
You have to be
careful, Timcampy.
This is really nasty.
Should we wait it out here
until the storm dies down?
Well, we can't predict that
it actually will die down.
Are you going to search?
Of course I'm going to search--
that's why we were sent here...
I'm not going to waste
time sitting around.
But...
Don't worry about it--in fact,
why don't you just wait
around and build a snowman,
Short Stack?
Hold on!
This is going to be
one of those stories
where we all freeze to death
and they don't find our bodies
until the snow
melts in the spring!
Like these two?
Sir, can you hear me?
Come on, wake up!
Are you able to move?
Is my father alright?
I think so... He seems fine.
We should carry them
to shelter immediately.
We... We've been
staying at a nearby inn.
Don't worry,
we'll take you there.
Then I'll keep going.
I'm quite sure they
don't need all five of us
to rescue them from some snow.
Hey, wait--
It's fine...
Don't worry, we'll
start searching again
as soon as we can
get them to safety.
In the meantime,
I'll go with Kanda.
We'll catch up to you.
I'm so sorry...
You're very kind.
You should
go ahead and rest now.
Ah, this gentleman seems to
have avoided any frostbite.
I asked the landlord's wife to
make something warm for you.
You didn't have to...
Father, see how good it looks?
Well... We'll be
right downstairs
so if you decide you need
anything else just call on us.
What do you think
a father and daughter
would be doing out in
a snowstorm like that?
Hmm.
I know why they're out there.
They went looking
for the "Leaf of Revival"
just like everybody
else is doing...
It's a legend here.
Wait... "Teeth"?
No, not "teeth," leaf!
The "Leaf of Revival"
is a peculiar
and mysterious item that
appears in Norse mythology.
Legend has it that
the hero Sigmund
originally discovered it...
The leaf can supposedly
return the lives
of those who passed
away before their time...
It is said that families
around the world
have been looking
for the Leaf of Revival
for hundreds of
years without success.
Even today many
still search for it...
It's hard to believe
but some poor people
are still looking for that
thing to this very day,
and for some bothersome reason,
every time they
come around here,
the weather turns on its head.
It's cleared up!
Yeah...
Is it just me or does
this wind feel warm?
Do you know where Bookman is?
He said he was tired
so he went to lie down.
I think that this extreme
weather is getting to him...
I forget that old
panda's age sometimes.
Well, we might as well go.
The wind seems to be
coming from that direction,
so if we travel
towards its source
maybe we'll stumble
upon the Innocence...
C'mon let's hurry...
Well aren't you a smart one...
Hello, how are
you this morning...?
I'm sorry again for all the
trouble we caused you yesterday.
Are you sure it's a good idea
for you to come outside so soon?
We'll manage.
I won't let you and your friends
find the Leaf before we do.
Oh... Um, we aren't
really looking for--
Go get ready... right now.
Whoa, where can we get those?!
It's almost hot
out today, father.
I know.
You still in one piece?
Yeah, I'm okay
You didn't hurt
yourself, did you?
No, I'm fine.
Well that's good...
Listen...
Yes?
We were told that
even the locals
won't set foot
beyond this point...
It could be very dangerous
to wander around here.
Maybe you two should
head back to the inn.
So you and your group can
have it all to yourselves...?
Let's go, Elda.
We're not looking for the "Leaf
of Revival," sir, I promise...
I can't tell you what it is,
but we're searching
for something else.
The truth is that Lavi
and I are Exorcists,
clergymen sent with the
power to destroy Akuma.
You're Exorcists?
Oh, Akuma...?
Hmmph! Those creatures
don't even exist.
Excuse me, but if the
Leaf of Revival exists,
why can't Akuma?
Please sir, you
should go back...
Trying to resurrect a
person you've lost
will only lead to regret
and there's also an evil
presence in the world
who will take advantage
of those desires.
And what would you
know of it, boy?!
No, Father, please!
Lavi, we should get going.
Stay close, Elda,
we're following them.
I have a feeling they're
hiding something.
So, did Skin go off
to look for Innocence?
I don't know... but
I wouldn't worry about him.
Why'd he take Lero with him?
I wanna play with Lero...
You're awfully whiny
this evening,
is something the matter?
Put that book down and
let's do something fun!!
There's nothing to do
without Lero around!
I'm so bored I'm gonna die!
Tyki, play with us
now so we don't die.
What?
He really really wants you
to play with him, see...?
He says "Play, Play
with me Tyki"!
It's alright, lero...
I'll just mind my own
business and read, lero.
May I stop...?
This isn't very fun.
Noooo!
Now catch!
Found it yet?
No.
Don't screw around!
But Skin, we're trying...
Are you arguing with me?!
No... I'm sorry!
I don't want your
damn apologies,
I want you to find it!
Of course, and we will!
We'll do our best, Skin!
Yeah, let's... let's go.
What? Do you have something
you want to say to me umbrella?
No, I don't, lero.
How did the hot
wind turn into this?!
Unbelievable.
I wonder where Kanda
is--you think he's alright?
You know at this point,
I'm really not as
worried about Kanda
as I am about that
Finder who went with him.
Look...
Maybe we should stop for now,
if we keep going
and they don't make it,
we'll just end up
having to carry them
to the inn on our
backs all over again.
Here.
Oh... thank you very much.
You're really prepared!
Since my Father prefers to
do so many things on his own,
I decided I should learn about
helpful ways of
supporting him...
Here... have some, Father.
You shouldn't talk to them.
Excuse me, but you're
the ones following us.
Father, why don't you
try to get some sleep,
just until the storm
calms down... okay?
She really is well-prepared...!
Hey, you realize if we get lost
we're going to have to
cuddle or something.
Allen?
Please feel free
to go on ahead...
Don't worry about us,
we'll manage just fine,
and I'm so sorry for
all of the rude things
my father said to you.
It's okay.
Don't tell him,
but I don't believe, the
Leaf of Revival exists...
I'm just... hoping that this
will make him feel better.
He's been really hard on himself
ever since the day my brother
was taken away from us.
So it's your brother
that he hopes
to revive and bring back
to life with the leaf...
You see... our house
had caught fire...
The four of us...
We were all living there
together when it happened,
but my younger brother was born
with bad legs, and he couldn't--
Jacob, Jacob!
No...
Don't come in!
Jacob!
Don't...!
Father, get them
away from here...
Go!
No!
Since then...
...my Mother has been confined
to her bed and Father...
...has so many regrets
he can't even look at me.
I won't stop him again...
I give him the freedom
to do what he wants...
As much as I'm able I want to
spare Father more heartache.
I read that the hero
Sigmund accidentally
caused his own
son's tragic death,
but then... he was able
to bring him back to life,
by placing the Leaf of
Revival on the boy's body.
Elda... come on.
Shhh!
My, my... Are they Exorcists?
What?
I'm afraid we're
completely lost.
Yeah... would you mind
if we joined up with you?
We're lucky we found you,
we just didn't know
what would happen
if we were stranded
out here by ourselves.
You forget how easy it is
to lose your way in the dark.
Ain't that the truth...
if you could just point
us in the direction
of the main road
we'd appreciate it.
You're all Akuma...
show yourselves!
Did I mention how glad
I am your eye is healed up...?
It really is convenient.
I suppose we have no choice.
What the hell is that?!
Just stay back!
Tell us where the Innocence is!
You think that we'd
tell you guys...?
Now that's hilarious.
What did you say?!
Hurry...
Go now!
You bastard!
Innocence Activate!
That was quite a show,
but I wonder where your
little friends are off to?
Stop it!
Allen, behind you!
Big Hammer, Little Hammer...
Grow, Grow, Grow!
Lavi...!
Take Elda and Frey and
get them out of here!
Mugen...!
Bring forth calamity!
Netherworld Creature Ichigen!
Retreat!
Yeah... Yu is here!
Shut up.
Allen...?
Allen!
The snow covers everything,
and the Akuma's attacks
grow more intense.
And then,
the legendary tree with shining
leaves appears before us.
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"Beyond the Snowstorm."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul!