Are you two injured in any way?
Head nurse. We're okay.
Thank goodness.
But that was some jolt, huh?
No kidding. Is everyone
else all right?
We managed to stay in one piece.
But I can't say the
same for our supplies.
[LAVI]
No way!
Krory-kins managed to stay
asleep this entire time?
He's really out cold.
Lavi. Your arm is bleeding.
It must've gotten cut
when the lights shattered.
Does it hurt?
I've lived through
far worse than this.
There's no reason to act tough.
We're going to patch
you up right away.
Who's actin' tough?
It's just a scratch.
Oh?
I didn't realize you possessed
such medical expertise.
Do you?
Well, not exactly.
[HEAD NURSE]
Hold on a minute.
Lenalee. You can't walk
around here barefoot.
Please, wear my shoes.
Wait, but what about you?
I don't want you
getting hurt either.
You know, she's got
a point, head nurse.
I'll just lend her my boots
and you can keep yours.
Both of you.
Shut up and do as your told
or you're going to
make more work for me.
[LENALEE LAVI]
Sorry, head nurse!
[HEAD NURSE] Seriously, I was
wondering what it'd take
to get you to pay attention.
This job is no picnic.
Believe me, it's not easy
treating marytrs
and workaholics.
The patients always know more
than the nurses
and never listen.
The size should work for you.
How do they fit?
Wonderful. They're so warm.
I didn't forget
to wear my shoes.
I was going to see Hevlaska.
Synchronize with my Innocence.
I left them on purpose.
My feet, they feel warm.
So comfortable.
[HEAD NURSE]
Let's stay here, Lenalee.
It'll be all right. This awful
morning will be over soon.
And you'll see, you
didn't even need to worry
about your Innocence.
You understand how the
Chief feels, don't you?
[LENALEE]
You have to believe me!
I never meant to
hurt my brother.
That's the last thing
I ever wanted.
But what was I supposed to do?
He was crying. What could I do?
Maybe he thought I was angry
or trying to blame him.
But it's not like I'm
purposefully trying
to get killed!
I want to live. With my brother.
All the people I care about!
But in order to do that,
I have to keep fighting!
It's the only way.
And the more I do, I know
it'll end up hurting Komui.
I hate Innocence so much!
Why does it have to make
this life so complicated?
Why does my brother
have to suffer, too?
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A]
Lab 5 has been destroyed
and the enemy has
breached the exit!
Not good!
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A]
Target is a single Akuma
that has evolved to Level 4!
Level... 4?
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A]
The status of the Exorcists
in Lab 5 remains unknown!
Attention! We need talismans.
Science Section floor!
The Akuma has left Lab 5
and is currently moving towards
the Science Section level!
Chief. What do we do?
"Chief," huh?
[LEVEL 4]
What a lovely white Rose Cross.
Hello, Chief.
Leave this to us!
Make a run for it!
Talisman Activa--
So you're the one running the
show here at the Black Order.
I wonder. Is your head worth the
same as one of your Exorcists?
[ORDER MEMBERS shouting]
Damn it, Komui!
Invest in some higher
quality weapons.
What? How did you--?
Chief Komui, are you injured?
I'm fine.
[ORDER MEMBERS]
Talisman activate!
[KOMUI]
Set the output at maximum
and focus all
beams on the target.
Keep it surrounded
with no opening!
[ORDER MEMBERS]
Sir!
[giggling]
Oh, God.
It's laughing.
[KANDA]
Listen up, you two.
No matter what, stay back.
But... we can't.
Kanda, no! You don't
have your Innocence!
I'm not exactly easy to kill.
[HEVLASKA]
It's Hevlaska. Can you hear me?
Komui. You need to come find me.
I'll attract the
Level 4's attention.
When it's distracted, take
the Innocence from inside me.
Then leave this place!
Fortunately, the Ark's
portal still connects
the Headquarters to
the Asian Branch.
Save yourselves.
If you stay here longer,
casualties will
continue to grow.
With Innocence, there's hope.
The Order will live on.
Komui! Did you hear me?
Listen! This is our only option!
[ROUVELIER] Hevlaska, we can
still use Lenalee's power.
[HEVLASKA] Rouvelier?
No. It's too soon for her.
Too dangerous.
Exorcists aren't machines.
If she's not ready, attempting
synchronization could kill her.
If Innocence exists in
order to destroy the Akuma,
what's the point
of not utilizing it?
No. I refuse.
[ROUVELIER] Are you trying to
get yourself killed, Hevlaska?
[HEVLASKA] I've lived with the
Order for over a hundred years.
You know what that means to me,
Rouvelier. Everything.
[ALL gasp]
Rouvelier.
Lenalee. You're an
Exorcist, aren't you?
[ROUVELIER]
Follow me.
What's the plan, Komui?
Come in, Section Leaders!
I won't repeat this, so you'd
better listen carefully!
You are to evacuate
Headquarters!
Get all personnel
to the Asia Branch
through Portal 3 of the Ark!
Those are your orders!
Did he say "evacuate"?
[KOMUI] Since the
safety of the Exorcists
who're in Lab 5 is unknown,
our top priorities are to
protect the Innocence
and avoid annihilation.
Proceed at once! We're leaving!
Finders! Take the--
Well, you heard it.
They're using Hevlaska
to shield their retreat.
Are you just gonna stand there
and be completely useless?
You're hiding? While
an Akuma's loose?
The very enemy of Exorcists!
And it's your sole
purpose to kill it!
Well, then. Displeased?
Let go, Junior Bookman.
[HEAD NURSE]
Director,
you heard Chief Komui
order us to evacuate.
If you interfere, you'll be
exceeding your authority.
Don't forget the Order
belongs to the Central Agency.
And Exorcists are our property
to do with whatever we please.
But it doesn't give
you the right
to treat human beings like
they're cannon fodder!
Get out of here!
I demand you leave this room
and never come back!
Let's go, Lenalee.
Your evolved Innocence might
actually be able to stand up
to the strength of a Level 4.
Will you protect or cower
with these people?
Watch it.
You know that only Exorcists
are capable of defeating Akuma.
If they don't fight,
all is lost!
Stop it! Don't listen to him!
[ROUVELIER] Fulfill your duty.
Fight for the Order, Lenalee!
That's enough!
Are you an Exorcist,
or aren't you?
No. Lenalee.
But...
You can't. You're
hurt. Stay here.
I just want to say... Thank you.
[LENALEE]
Ever since that day,
when my brother came
to Headquarters,
I thought I'd be
trapped here forever.
I gave up any hope of leaving.
Ever running away.
It was on that day that
I became an Exorcist.
He sacrificed everything
to protect his sister.
His freedom. His future.
I'm the one who
imprisoned him here.
I became an Exorcist so
I could be with the one
who gave up everything for me.
That's right, Lenalee.
After all, you'll never
escape this place.
I'm so sorry.
[HEAD NURSE crying]
[HEAD NURSE] It isn't right.
Everything about this is wrong.
Ma'am.
[LAVI]
I know I have to follow her.
But is it just to
observe and record?
Or is it because--?
[LAVI]
Damn it!
Lavi!
[KOMUI]
Hurry up!
Get it as far away from
the Ark gate as possible!
[gasps]
You can't run away from me.
I'm going to get you.
[giggling]
[LEVEL 4] I bet there are humans
on the other side of this door.
I have to stop him or
everyone's going to be--
You can't even stand
up in your condition.
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A] The
central exit at Gate 3's hall
is now blocked.
Each section is to
evacuate immediately.
This is your opportunity!
Go to Hevlaska! Hurry, Chief!
[LEVEL 4]
Hm?
And where do you
think you're going?
You can't run from me.
Kanda! You need to evacuate!
Yeah, right.
Wait! If Kanda's going,
then I'm coming with you.
If you do, you'll regret it!
There's no way you're
going to stop me.
Hevlaska still has my Innocence.
If you came back empty
handed, I'd be pissed off.
Also, that barrier won't hold.
When it finally breaks,
I'll be your shield.
Will you be serious?
I am not going to let you
throw away your life!
Heh.
Then do your best
to stay outta trouble
and you won't have to
inconvenience me.
[HEVLASKA]
Hurry up, Komui.
You need to collect the
Innocence and cube within me.
You should know,
Rouvelier is on his way
here with Lenalee.
I'll beg Hevlaska.
Ask her to implant an
Innocence in my body.
[KOMUI]
Descend!
We're all counting
on you, Chief.
[giggles]
Looks like the Chief
want to play a game.
I'll give him ten seconds.
Ten.
[LAVI, LENALEE yelp]
[LAVI, LENALEE coughing]
We stopped.
Then why is everything moving?
The quake must've damaged it.
We made it farther
than I anticipated.
We'll take the stairs from here.
By the way, who invited
Bookman Junior?
I don't think anyone did.
Who? Me?
Huh. Is it for your records?
You Bookmen flock
to battlefields
like vultures to the dead.
But that's your mission.
You may do as you like.
Thanks a bunch.
Lavi.
I'm not gonna try
and stop you.
This is your decision and I
know you've made up your mind.
But... let me go with you.
[HEVLASKA]
Rouvelier! Stop!
Hm? Is this Hevlaska?
[HEVLASKA]
The Level 4 will be here soon.
We don't have
enough time to wait
for Lenalee and the Innocence
to properly synchronize!
We only require a moment.
All you need to worry about
is placing the Innocence
inside of her body.
[HEVLASKA]
You're not serious.
Dead serious, Hevlaska.
This request is from Lenalee.
Seems she's quite familiar
with the experiments
and wishes to have it
performed on herself.
What? I refuse her request!
I won't subject Lenalee to that.
She's one of our comrades!
Comrades?
Well, your leader is
giving you a direct order.
Or should I remind you
you've always done as
you were commanded?
Obeying for over 100 years.
Why is this occasion
any different?
You really believe
you're a saint?
[gasps]
You're murdering your family.
[ROUVELIER] I gave you a
direct order. Carry it out.
Save your questions.
We must hurry.
[BOOKMAN]
Malcolm C. Rouvelier.
You'll find several high-ranking
Central Agency officials
that share the same last name,
but he's the highest
of them all.
Since the beginning,
all the way back to the
founding of the Black Order,
the Rouveliers have always
held positions of power.
There's even a
record that states,
years ago one of their daughters
was offered as a Saint unto God.
But what became
of her after that
isn't written down
in any document.
Since then, because of their
kinship to that Saint,
the Rouveliers'
status is guaranteed,
but it also requires them
to undertake special tasks
for the Order.
[LAVI] There were experiments
performed on the blood relatives
of Accommodators'
here at headquarters.
That is, up until Komui
became the Chief.
Was that their special task?
Providing human guinea pigs for
experiments with Innocence?
Selecting their own family
members for a hundred years...
Director, what's the
reason you're here? Really.
What do you mean?
I'm only asking because
you sure seem anxious
to find Hevlaska.
I move swiftly to only one goal.
Defeating the Earl!
Zero.
[ORDER MEMBER F]
What was that noise?
It came from above us!
[LAVI]
Do you hear that?
[KANDA]
Get ready.
It's the Level 4!
Komui!
[yells]
[gasps]
Komui!
Big brother!
I'll go help them!
There may still be time!
[ROUVELIER]
Hm?
Is that--?
A Level 4. Come on,
Komui! Don't die!
Lavi. Brother.
[ROUVELIER]
With the elevator broken,
retrieving the Innocence
is off the table.
Hevlaska! Implant an
Innocence in her! Now!
[ORDER MEMBER G]
Wake up, Chief.
[KANDA]
Damn it, Komui.
[ORDER MEMBER F]
Chief.
[KOMUI] Blast. The elevator,
can it be repaired?
Looks like it's beyond saving.
Did you shield me?
You saved my life.
Shut up. It's nothing.
I can't belive it. Are you
all right, Chief Komui?
Yeah, I think so.
Did either one of
you get injured?
Don't worry. We're--
[LAVI]
Komui! Kanda!
Lavi?
What do you know?
You're still alive!
[KANDA]
Of course we are.
[KOMUI]
If Lavi's here, that means...
Lenalee!
[LEVEL 4] Does this mean
our little game of tag
is over, Chief?
If you're smart,
you'll fall back.
You gotta be kidding.
[ROUVELIER]
Stop delaying, Hevlaska.
Implant an Innocence
inside of her.
You're sure about this?
I'm prepared.
Yes, I want this.
It's all right.
I'm sorry, Komui.
Get it over with.
Hevlaska!
[ROUVELIER]
Hevlaska! Hevlaska!
[LEVEL 4]
How lucky can I be?
There's even more humans
here than I thought.
[LAVI]
Damn it.
[KOMUI]
Lenalee.
[LENALEE]
Big brother.
It's... so close.
[LENALEE]
My vision's getting blurry.
It's no use.
Please.
God, I've hated you for so
long, but hear me, please.
I'm begging you...
Give me strength.
Never before in my life
have I wanted Innocence
as much as I do now.
[ALLEN]
As our final moments draw near,
Lenalee says one
last prayer to God,
begging for her
Innocence to return.
Is her wish going to be granted
or will it fall on deaf ears?
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The Promise."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
Principal Earl.
I've successfully infiltrated
the class without suspicion.
[LEVEL 4 chuckles]