Exorcists...
Chosen, by God Himself...
They exist to destroy the evil
that lurks in the darkness...
an evil that brings pain and
suffering to the world.
Who... Who in their right mind
would build a headquarters
in a place like this?
I finally made it...
Exorcist Headquarters...
The Black Order.
Creepy.
You know I'd heard about
these headquarters before,
but... how can I put this...?
I'm getting a spooky
feeling about this place.
There's only one way
to find out, isn't there?
All right, well
here goes nothing.
Who's the kid?
Well, I'm not sure, but he
did make it up the cliff.
He's walking to the door!
Why is there a
child out there...?
You know we don't
tolerate outsiders...
Someone go out there
and push the kid off.
I don't think that'd
be a good idea...
Judging from the look of him
I seriously doubt he
just wandered here.
Hey Brother, check this out.
Look at that marking.
That's General Cross' Golem...
See?
She's right everyone.
Hello? Anyone home?
My name's Allen Walker
and I was referred here
by General Cross Marian...
I'm here to request a meeting
with an executive of the Order.
He's General Cross' apprentice?
I thought that the
General was dead?
The kid said he's
here on referral...
Do you know anything
about that, Chief Komui?
Afraid not.
Well...
Have the Gatekeeper
do a physical exam.
Oh, hello.
Prepare for an X-ray
exam to determine
if you are a human or Akuma!
What's wrong with this thing?
I can't get a reading.
Failure!!!
What?!
He has the mark!
The mark of evil on his face!
He fails!
A pentacle is the
mark of an Akuma...!
He's a minion for
the Millennium Earl!
He's come to kill us!!
He's a spy! A spy!
Hey... Don't we have an
exorcist around here?
Very funny Reever.
Kanda's already on the move.
You're either
fearless or stupid
for showing your
face here alone.
Hold on!
I think there's been
a misunderstanding!!
Mighty Mugen, unsheathe!
He damaged my Anti-Akuma Weapon!
You all right...?
Your arm is about to explode.
It's my Anti-Akuma Weapon...
After all I am an exorcist.
Huh?
Gatekeeper!
But he has a
pentacle on his face...!
Just because he says he's
human doesn't mean he is...!
I'd rather be safe than sorry!
But I am a human you idiot!
I admit that I'm cursed,
but I'm an exorcist!
I swear it's true!
That's enough.
The only way to know
for sure is to cut you open!
Prepare to be slaughtered...
...by the mighty Mugen!
What...?
Wait, I'm telling you
people the truth
and I can prove it, believe me!
There should have
been a referral letter
sent b-b-b-b-by
Master Cross himself!
A letter...
from the General?
Yeah.
It was addressed to
some guy named Komui.
Hey you! Over there!
Ye... Yes, sir?
Find the letter!
It's on my desk!
It may take awhile.
That's a tall order, Chief.
Are you serious Komui?
I'll give you a hand!
Oh crap!
That's not it...
Neither is that...
And it's not that one...
Here! I found it!
It's addressed
from General Cross!
Read it man!
Dear Komui...
I will be sending a kid
named Allen Walker to you.
Take good care of him...
Oh crap.
Great... Sounds good to me...
Hey there, Reever...
You should stop Kanda.
I gotta go refill my coffee.
Maybe you could clean up
your office on the way there!!
Kanda! I need you
to stand down!
Stop the attack!
He's friendly!
I repeat: He's friendly!
Lenalee.
Hey...
What's up?
Do your brother a favor and
help me get ready, would you?
With what?
It looks like we're going
to be having a visitor.
Fine... OPEN!!!
So the kid was sent by Cross.
Sounds like a perfect
candidate for appraisal.
Allen Walker.
Your access has been granted.
Hey Komui...
Mind filling me in?
Sorry about that.
The kid checks out.
He's General Cross' apprentice.
Plus, having Timcanpy with him
is proof enough,
wouldn't you say?
Give credit where
credit is due, sir.
Okay... Section Leader...
Let's apoligize.
But I didn't do anything wrong!
Let him go, Kanda.
He's one of us.
Please...? Please, please,
please please please?
Kanda, stop it!
Enough with the
macho head-games.
Now you two get inside
before I close the gate.
I said to get in.
Nice meeting you.
I'm Lenalee, the
Chief's Assistant.
Uhh... Kanda?
Uh... Please tell me
I got your name right.
No hard feelings?
What fool would
actually shake your hand
knowing that you're cursed.
Don't mind him...
He's been on edge since he got
back from his last assignment.
Look at the new guy.
He looks like he's
twelve years old.
But if he's so young,
then what's with his hair?
It's pure white.
Rumor is he's cursed.
It'll be interesting to
see how he handles the job.
Yeah but innocence has
nothing to do with age.
So this is it...
The Black Order.
And here's the dining hall.
This entire floor is
the training area...
It consists of
three different layers.
Here's the lounge...
And there's also the
sanatorium, a library,
and the dormitory
for the staff...
I can show you those later.
If they're not on assignments,
this is where exorcists
spend all their time...
In fact most of them
start calling our
headquarters their home.
That's nice...
Just like... a family.
Though every once in a while
someone leaves on purpose,
but it's rare.
Like Master Cross.
Where is General Cross?
You two went to India
at some point, right?
We did... about
three months ago.
Allen, sit down.
Yes... Master.
Can you believe it's
been three years
since you became
my apprentice...?
You've shown enormous
progress in your path
to becoming an exorcist.
That's why as of
today you can officially
call yourself a full-fledged
professional exorcist.
Are you serious?
Sort of.
First you have to agree
on paying a visit
to the Exorcist
Headquarters for me.
Wait, you... do know where
Headquarters are, don't you?
Yeah.
I'll leave Timcanpy with you.
I've already sent a
referral letter earlier today
to an executive named Komui...
So leave first thing
in the morning.
Let me guess...
You're not coming
with me... are you?
Hell no. I'd rather lose a
thumb than go back there!
Wait, so your Master knocked you
unconscious and then ran off?
Yeah.
Where are we now?
I'll let my brother answer that.
Ouh, hello there...!
I am Komui Lee...
Chief of the Science Division!
On behalf of the staff
I'd like to welcome you.
And sorry about the trouble
earlier. What a pain
Don't look at us!!
Come over here and put
your arm under the light.
Huh?
I understand you received
some damage earlier...
You know when Kanda
attacked you unprovoked.
You shouldn't have
to endure such pain.
Just as I thought. The
nerve system is damaged.
Lenalee, anesthesia.
For the boy.
Okay.
Can you activate it?
Uh... sure.
Activate.
Interesting...
You're a Parasite Type.
Wait, I'm... a what?
Yes... Anyone who
can turn their body
into a weapon has a type...
Your parasitic type is
one of the rarest forms
of all Anti-Akuma Weapons.
So...
I don't think I want to
know what that thing is for.
Aww... afraid...?
You shouldn't be because
when I get done with you,
you'll be good as new,
though I must warn you,
this will be traumatic.
Hold on!
Now!
I hate that sound.
I feel for the poor kid.
Sorry about that.
My brother has a habit
of getting carried away.
I... didn't realize this
guy was related to you.
You're going there
after this, aren't you...?
Wouldn't it be a good
idea to make sure
that he's human before you
go through the process?
Not this time...
I know he's human.
How is that?
It's simple...
Humans are the only
species known to man
to be susceptible to curses.
Your arm is fixed, but you'll
have to wait until tomorrow
for the anesthesia to wear
off before you use it.
I need to make sure to
never break my arm again.
Don't get down on yourself.
The advantages of
being a Parasite Type
far outweigh the negatives.
Having that ability
makes you part of
the chosen ones who can best
utilize the power of Innocence.
Innocence?
God's Innocence, to be exact...
The unbridled power
of omnipotence.
I don't understand.
Once again, God has
graced us with his presence.
The Great Generals...
These are the gentlemen
we answer to.
Now show them how
worthy your unique abilities
will be towards the cause.
Show... me...
your Innocence.
What are you doing?!
You're wasting your strength.
That arm will be useless
until the anesthetic
wears off tomorrow.
Komui!
So what do you think,
Hevlaska...?
Does this Apostle of God meet
your exact level of standards?
What are they doing to me...?
It feels weird...
As if something is
probing my insides.
Come on...
Activate!
Just do it!
Never activate your weapon
when your nerves are
not yet fully recovered...
Try to relax...
I'm not your enemy.
Two percent...
Sixteen percent...
Thirty-one percent...
Fifty-seven percent...
Eighty-three percent.
It appears that
eighty-three percent
is the maximum synchro-rate you
and your weapon are capable of.
What's synchro-rate?
The number indicates
your ability level
when activating your
Anti-Akuma Weapon...
The lower the synchro-rate,
the more difficulty
you'll have activating,
putting you at a higher risk
for permanent damage.
I apologize.
I didn't mean to scare you...
The only way I can accurately
gauge your Innocence...
is through touch.
What exactly can you
learn from my Innocence?
Allen Walker...
In the future, when darkness
dominates this planet,
your Innocence will produce
an extraordinary
"Destroyer of Time."
A time... destroyer?
I have no idea what that means
but it sounds amazing...!
Hevlaska's prophecies are
cryptic, but they are true.
Congrats kid!
Now we can actually trust you!
Mind putting that
down so I can hit you?
Settle down...
It's our policy...
An involuntary Innocence
check is required...
That's something
I would have liked
to have been told
when I first walked in!!
So what else is there
to know about Innocence?
Tell me everything.
I was about to
explain it to you...
What I'm about to
tell you is secret.
Information only known
within the Black Order...
and to those involved
with the Millennium Earl.
It all started around
a century ago...
when a golden cube was
discovered within the Earth.
To the future
inhabitants of Earth...
We are the ones who
defeated the darkness,
but our society
soon fell into ruin.
This message is a warning...
Avoid the cataclysmic
disaster we have endured...
Heed our words, we
have little time left.
What we found inside the cube...
was a prophecy from
an ancient civilization...
and a set of
implicit instructions.
But... for what?
For the material
the cube is made of...
It's called the God Crystal.
Its power is astonishing...
And it is what we prefer
to call Innocence...
The material embedded
in your left hand
is made from the God Crystal.
Anti-Akuma Weapons
are Innocence that's been
processed into a useable form.
The original creators
of the cube battled
the Millennium Earl
with Innocence.
The Earl?!
They used it to
destroy the Earl...
but in the end, they destroyed
themselves as well...
This was referred to as Noah's
Flood in the Old Testament.
However the prophecy
inside the cube referred
to it as the "three
days of darkness."
The cube's prophecy also says...
that the world will come
to an end once more...
at the hands of
the Millennium Earl.
So just as predicted...
the Millennium Earl
has returned to the Earth.
The Black Order was created
to avert the coming disaster.
Gather Apostles.
Gather accommodators.
Without accommodators,
Innocence is
incapable of activating.
These accommodators the
Generals speak of are Exorcists.
However...
To counteract the
power of the Exorcists,
the Millennium Earl created
Akuma's to hunt them down.
At its most basic level,
Innocence is created
by light energy,
whereas Akuma's are
created using dark energy.
As the Akuma's
do his dirty work,
the Earl searches the earth
for pieces of
Innocence to destroy.
To the best of our knowledge,
there are one-hundred-nine
pieces of Innocence
scattered around the world...
Now, it's our duty to
collect these pieces
before the Earl does...
If we fail to
do so, it will lead
to the annihilation
of the entire human race.
We need your help... Allen.
If we are unable to
win this holy war,
the cube's prophecy
will become a reality,
and the world as we know
it will cease to exist.
You must fight.
This is your destiny as
one who was chosen...
by Innocence.
It is your duty.
I'm looking forward to
working together with you...
Just know that the pay is awful.
Right.
Welcome to the Black Order.
Most of our active
exorcists aren't here...
They're currently
in various places
around the world
on assignment...
But you'll meet
them before long.
You should know Hevlaska
here is one of our exorcists.
I've been around a long
time... as guardian...
Ever since the Black Order was
established a century ago...
Allen...
May God's divine
protection be with you.
Wait a minute, I wonder
what happened to Timcanpy?
Never stop...
Keep walking.
I've come so far, Mana...
I'm finally at
the starting point.
I promise...
I will never stop, no matter
what's put in front of me...
I'll continue the journey
until the very end.
The ancient town of Mater...
Reports were flooding
in of a ghost sighting,
but when we arrived,
the screams of Finders
were the only thing
we could hear.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The Ghost of Mater."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.