[panting]
How's Miranda holding up?
Poor thing's beyond exhausted.
I wish she could get some decent
sleep, but right now that's...
...kinda difficult,
to say the least.
Yeah.
Our top priority is to find and
rendezvous with General Cross
as soon as possible.
[CHOMESUKE]
Land up ahead!
[ALL gasp]
[BOOKMAN]
Uh?
We made it.
[CHOMESUKE]
Watch your step now.
Welcome to... Japan!
[BOOKMAN]
Japan is located in the far east
and is known as a
"closed country."
They've rejected trade
and interference
from the outside world
for nearly 300 years.
When you think about it,
the island makes for
the perfect hideout.
I wouldn't be a bit
surprised if the Earl
is the reason for that
300 year isolation.
Precisely.
What?!
And, who are you?
Don't you recognize me?
What about my voice?
Well. You sound familiar.
You're aren't... Chomesuke?
We got a winner.
[LAVI]
Wow! What a total babe!
[gasps]
[LAVI]
Get a hold of yourself, Lavi!
Chomesuke's an Akuma!
An adorable Akuma!
[LAVI groans, screams]
Such a novice.
[CHOMESUKE]
The Earl uses Japan as his base
to send Akuma into the world.
If you fought it, chances
are it deployed from here.
Then why doesn't the
government take action?
And how can this all go
unnoticed by the people?
It's difficult to stop when 90%
of the country's population
is made up of Akuma.
Make no mistake, the Earl
is the true emperor here.
Ninety?
Three centuries
under the Earl's rule.
Sounds like this is his own
island paradise. That's great.
There's not a single
place in this country
that's safe for humans.
You'd have to be
crazy to stay here.
But then again, it's not exactly
hospitable to Akuma either.
Hospitable? What do
you mean by that?
[gasps]
Something's up ahead!
[ALL gasp]
Sachiko.
[gasps] Kawamura! Here!
Make yourself useful!
[LAVI]
Uh? Who's "Sachiko"?
[CHOMESUKE] It's my name
when I'm in human form.
And that's my friend, Kawamura.
She's an Akuma that's also been
modified by General Cross!
Another one?
[CHOMESUKE]
Kawamura!
You have no idea how glad
I am you came to meet us!
It's perfect timing!
Speaking of which, I didn't
know how much I had left!
[KAWAMURA grunting]
Is something wrong?
[grunting continues]
[gagging]
[gasps] No! Kawamura!
[ALL gasp]
Chomesuke?
[screams]
Run for it! Now!
[ALL gasp]
I told you to run for it! Hurry
up and blow out that lantern!
[ALL gasp]
Those are Level Threes.
A trio.
Don't breathe, you hear me?
Otherwise, we're dead.
Just hide your presence
the best you can.
Explain to me what's going on.
And what happened to
that friend of yours?
Kawamura must've been ambushed
on her way to meet us.
We can't do anything now
that she's been captured
by those Level Threes.
She's as good as dead.
Captured? Why would Akuma
trap their own kind?
[roars]
[screams]
--[KAWAMURA screams]
--[ALL gasp]
[CHOMESUKE]
Because they're hungry.
When their population
density is abnormally high
within a district, this kind
of phenomenon happens.
In order to control their
impulse to kill humans,
they consume other Akuma and
absorb their abilities instead.
But me? I'm just a Level Two.
No way I can defeat them!
t's the same for both
humans and Akuma in Japan.
Only the strong survive.
Kill or be killed.
Huh? What did you just say?
[CELL]
I can't erase his name!
Allen Walker's name
won't come off!
No matter how many times
I scrub, it remains.
So persistent.
You're just not scrubbing
hard enough!
Put some back into it!
Or maybe you're lying to me
to get yourself out
of that cage sooner!
He's still alive.
Allen Walker lives.
Huh...?
[CELL sobs]
[footsteps]
[DEVIT]
Well... Well...
[TYKI]
Huh?
[DEVIT]
What do we have here?
A sharply dressed degenerate
sitting by a pond feasting
on carp. I thought you
were supposed to be
on a special mission right now.
Great. It's the twins.
Name's Devit.
I'm Jasdero!
[BOTH]
And together we're Jasdevi!
You look like two poorly
dressed cadavers.
This is makeup, idiot!
It's called style!
Why don't you boys
just scurry along.
I'm kind of in the
middle of a thought.
We know why you're in Japan.
The Earl gave you a list of
people you're supposed to kill,
didn't he? And the rumor is
your next target is close by.
That's what we heard!
Yeah.
I'm supposed to kill a Cross
something or another.
General Cross the exorcist is
our target and don't forget it,
fish breath! Touch him and
we'll add you to our kill list!
We'll kill you! Kill you!
[TYKI]
Huh?
[JASDERO grunting]
[TYKI]
So I'm not alone.
It would appear we're
all part of this mission
to kill the Generals.
But Cross is still
alive, isn't he?
What's taking you so long?
Piss off. Cross is unusually
tough and slippery.
We've already tried killing him
thrice and failed each time!
We're failures!
Failures! [laughs]
From what I understand,
your last target also has
a problem staying dead.
What was his name?
Allen something?
Oh, shut up.
So, where exactly are we headed?
Just going to meet with the
Millennium Earl and Road.
Uh? Really?
[growling]
[crash]
[groaning]
Hey. You just ran
over something.
[JASDERO]
What?! I didn't see anything!
If the Earl and Road are here,
that must mean...
the "box" is done.
Yeah. Probably.
So, tell us what brings you
to Japan, sweet tooth.
The name's Skinn.
Not "sweet tooth".
I'm only here 'cause the
General I was assigned to kill
fled to this country.
I'm just tightening
the noose, that's all!
Ah. You failed too.
Does anyone else get that
the impression the four of us
are about to get fired?
[SKINN]
I'm just tightening the noose!
[DEVIT]
I'm nothing like you two!
[JASDERO laughs]
The boss isn't gonna like this!
[JASDERO laughing]
[LAVI groans] I feel sick.
Think I'm gonna throw up.
[KRORY]
It's savage.
[BOOKMAN] To imagine Akuma feed
on each other with such frenzy.
[LENALEE grunts]
Are you all right?
I can go and fetch
some water if you want.
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
I'm sorry. What's your name?
You can just call me Chaozii.
I was a third-class
sailor on the ship.
Over there, we have
Maosa on the left.
And that's Kie on the right.
If you need anything,
you can count on us.
Good. Likewise.
[gulps]
[CHOMESUKE] This is bad.
I'm getting thirsty...
[KRORY, LAVI]
Uh?
Somethin' wrong, Sachiko?
Chomesuke is fine, thanks.
So what options do we have?
There are no options.
I'm gonna have to guide you
to Edo myself, so let's go!
[CHOMESUKE] And quick...
I don't have much time left.
[LAVI grunts]
[KRORY]
Hm?
[CHOMESUKE]
The Ark!
Now what, Sachiko?
You jerk! What did I tell you?
Call me Chomesuke!
What am I doing?
We don't have time to argue
about something so trivial!
Huh?
[CHOMESUKE gasping]
Chomesuke!
[CHOMESUKE groaning]
[CHOMESUKE]
Get out of here!
[LAVI, KRORY]
Chomesuke!
[AKUMA A laughs]
What a tasty dish.
[laughing]
[AKUMA A laughing]
Smart of me to wait for my food.
At first, when I smelled humans,
I thought it was just a pleasant
memory of a past meal.
Look at you delicacies.
You're not from this
country, are you?
More importantly...
...why is a pack of humans
on such friendly terms
with this Akuma?
[CHOMESUKE groans]
[LAVI]
Let her go!
[AKUMA A] How lovely.
I get dinner and a show!
[LAVI]
Are you alone?
[AKUMA A]
Of course.
[LAVI] What happened
to your two friends?
[AKUMA A] You humans will
never understand us.
[gasps]
The relief that only comes
from killing your kind.
Like quenching a thirst.
[CHOMESUKE gasping]
[AKUMA A]
I have the opportunity
to torture humans again. Why
would I want to share that?
[AKUMA A laughs]
Now. Time for the first course!
[yells]
[footsteps]
[TYKI]
So many memories.
I've only been here
a handful of times,
but it always manages to
fill with me nostalgia.
And I wasn't even born here.
I hear ya. It makes me
feel that way too.
The weird thing is I don't even
go for gloomy places like this.
Your genes are incapable
of forgettin',
and will always remind you
from whence you came.
[MILLENNIUM EARL chuckles]
[MILLENNIUM EARL] After all,
it was here that the Noah
survived the Great Flood
and sowed the seeds
of the second generation
of mankind.
We're standing where
the original descendants
of Noah were born.
Didn't I explain all
this to you before?
This place is the home
of all humankind.
But we call it by
another name...
...Noah's Ark.
[NARRATOR]
The story of Noah's Ark is told
in chapters six through nine
in the Book of Genesis
of the Old Testament.
In case it's needed,
here's a recap:
[MILLENNIUM EARL] When God saw
how wicked humans had become,
he vowed to destroy the
world with a great flood.
But a man named Noah was
allowed to build an ark
so he and his family
might be spared.
They were the only survivors.
The ark drifted across the ocean
until it came to rest
upon Mount Ararat.
It was there, God bestowed
Noah with a new covenant
and commanded him,
like Adam before,
to go forth and
replenish the earth.
Or so it's written in the
Holy Books of the great faiths.
[TYKI]
Hm. So this is home.
Only now it's been turned
into a factory for Akuma.
Humans and Akuma share the
same birthplace. How ironic.
[laughs] Hilarious!
[laughing] Unfortunately
the time approaches
when we must say farewell
to this ark forever.
And, good-bye to Edo.
We need to prepare for
the impending Ragnarok.
And that will require a ship
with different specifications.
A brand new model.
[chanting]
By the way. Since you're here,
I assume you've successfully
accomplished your missions?
[ALL]
Uh! Mostly.
I'll prepare a banquet
for us to share.
Then we can discuss your
failures in greater detail.
[LAVI yelling]
[LAVI]
Fire Stamp!
[chuckles]
As expected from a Level Three.
[AKUMA A]
It's useless!
[LAVI screams]
[AKUMA A laughing]
[LAVI screams, grunts]
[KRORY]
My turn!
[growls]
Did you lose your appetite?
[KRORY grunts]
[AKUMA A chuckles]
Uh?
[AKUMA A]
Try these!
[KRORY groaning]
[LAVI]
Krory! No!
[LENALEE]
Enough. I have to help!
[LENALEE gasping]
You can't fight!
You guys make a run for it.
[CHAOZII]
What?
We'll hold them back until
you can escape to safety.
Go! Now!
And where are we
supposed to run to?
There's nowhere on this island
that's safe for us to hide!
But...
We came along to help you.
We're not going to abandon you
when the fighting starts.
[MAOSA, KIE grunt]
For the sake of our
comrades who died,
we'll work until death!
Just say the word. We'll lay
our lives on the line!
There's no need.
Let's all survive so
we can back together.
[AKUMA A]
Take this! And this! And this!
[LAVI, KRORY grunting]
[AKUMA A] You're not
challenging me at all.
At least put some
spirit in it. [laughs]
I've got an idea.
If I eat this one first, will
you be more motivated to fight?
Don't you dare!
[AKUMA A laughs]
[CHOMESUKE groaning]
You bastard!
[BOOKMAN]
Stop!
What for?!
Look.
[CHOMESUKE]
What are you waiting for, Lavi?
This is your chance! You can
escape while he's focused on me!
[gasps] Chomesuke...
Go. Now.
There's no way!
Calm yourself, Lavi. Think.
[LAVI]
I am thinking.
Huh?
We may escape this time,
but other Akuma
are gonna find us.
We need Chomesuke as a guide,
or we'll never make
it to Edo alive.
[BOOKMAN grunts]
[LAVI yells]
Innocence. Level Two... Release!
[LAVI yelling]
[LAVI]
Devouring Flame... Fire Stamp!
How many times are you planning
on trying the same trick?
[CHOMESUKE yelps]
[CHOMESUKE]
Lavi!
You saved my life!
I thought I was dead!
Thank you!
Stop... I can't breathe...
[chuckles] While that was
a bit of unexpected fun,
there's no end to the amount
of webs I can produce! See?
I'm getting bored and hungry.
And so, I think I'll end this.
[AKUMA A laughing]
[blade slicing]
[AKUMA A]
Huh?
[AKUMA grunt]
[AKUMA B]
Just as I thought.
[AKUMA C] Look who's
sneaking behind our back.
Ha, ha. There they are.
[KRORY, CHOMESUKE]
Hm?
I see.
Not only was your Fire Stamp
effective against the web,
it worked as signal to
lure the other Akuma.
Our opponent said
it best himself.
He didn't want his friends
complicating matters.
But I didn't want 'em
to feel left out,
so I thought I'd
extend an invitation
for them to join
our dinner party.
You figured you'd just eat them
all and not share with us?!
[grunts] The strong survive
and weaklings like you perish.
You're weak!
Just 'cause you're
not a Level Two
doesn't mean you're safe from
getting devoured by us!
Huh? Is that so? You think
I'm on the menu tonight?
It's fine by me.
You're dead!
Uncivilized.
If you're willing to kill
your own to prove strength,
you aren't fit to be called
allies in the first place.
[CHOMESUKE]
Hey! I found a way out!
There's a path
through the forest!
We can all escape while
they're distracted
but there's no time to waste!
Hurry before they notice us!
[JASDERO, DEVIT chewing]
This isn't sweet.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Of course not, Skinn.
I don't even want to imagine
something so vile.
[sighs] I'm growing weary
of raw fish these days.
I would hardly put pond
carp on the same level.
Wait. You were watching me?
[laughs]
Well anyway, I haven't
seen Road at all today.
I thought she was going
to be joining us.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Don't you worry about Road.
She's busy preparing
for the move. [laughs]
[CHOMESUKE] Looks like
if we follow this route
it'll lead us to Edo.
[LAVI]
Just as I thought.
[CHOMESUKE]
But if we take it,
I can't guarantee
any of your safety.
It's still not too late
to turn back around.
If they find us again, we won't
have a chance of surviving!
Regardless, we have to
keep pushing forward.
I agree.
[BOOKMAN]
Mm.
That's the reason
we came to Japan,
and we're not giving up now.
[ALL grunt]
[sighs] In that case,
stay close and follow me.
Try to keep up.
Watch out, Edo!
We're on our way!
[ALLEN] Despite the best
efforts from everyone
at the Asian Branch, it
simply isn't enough.
My Innocence fails to revive.
Only anxiety and frustration
grow in its place.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"Confusion and Impatience."
I already told you, Road.
I'm not gonna help you
with your homework.
[LERO]
Not, Lero!
Jeez...
[JASDERO, DEVIT]
Heh, heh.
Don't judge them.
They ain't sweet,
but they're friends.