[SUMAN, RIDO, LAVONG panting]
[RIDO]
Innocence! Activate!
[LAVONG]
[LAVONG yells]
[gasps]
[TYKI chuckles]
[LAVONG whimpering, yells]
[TYKI]
Hardly a challenge.
The only pleasure I'll receive
is killing you one by one.
[LAVONG whimpering]
[LAVONG screams]
[SUMAN]
Bring the Wind!
[SUMAN grunts]
[LAVONG yelling]
[LAVONG yells]
[LAVONG gasping]
[LAVONG screams]
[TYKI laughs] Step up.
Who's ready to die next?
[BOTH whimper]
[RIDO yells]
--[RIDO groans]
--[splash]
[TYKI] Kazarna Rido. Charcar
Lavong. And Daisha Barry.
I'm accumulating a nice pile.
Although I do find
it disappointing
that none of your names
are on my list.
[SUMAN whimpers]
But, wait, what's
your name, good sir?
[SUMAN gasps]
No! Stay away!
[SUMAN whimpers]
I don't wanna die!
Someone! Help me, please!
Well. Looks like
he's finally awake.
Hey, mister. You feel okay?
[FAN'S MOTHER] He's probably
too thirsty to speak.
Fan. Go fetch some water.
Okay!
[crash]
[growling]
[WORKERS chattering]
[CREW A]
Hurry up, people!
The longer you take, the later
we ship out, now move it!
Let's get that food stored
below deck on the double!
Careful there. We haven't
even set sail yet.
[CREW D]
Yes, ma'am!
[MAHOJA]
Luck is on our side.
We've finished checking the
engine. No problems were found.
Once the crew finishes loading
the remaining supply of food
and water, we can
depart at any time.
See if we can move faster.
I'd prefer if we left
as soon as possible.
Whatever you desire, Master.
I can't thank you enough.
There's really no need
for gratitude.
As supporters of the Black Order
you can always count on us
to assist the Exorcists,
whatever the cost.
Even so, the voyage
will be treacherous.
I'm aware of the risks.
As was Marian before
he took his voyage.
[LENALEE]
That's right.
The ship General Cross was
aboard was sunk by Akuma.
It was a despicable
act ordered by
the Millennium Earl and
the Noah who are trying
to destroy the shard of
Innocence called the Heart.
The Heart,
it's the source of the power
of all the Innocence pieces.
And has the ability to
reduce them to rubble.
If the Millennium Earl
recovers the Heart before us
and destroys it, all
the shards of Innocence
around the world
will be shattered.
No need to look worried.
I know Cross Marian and I
guarantee it would take more
than some shipwreck
to keep him dead.
Allen was his apprentice
so he understands.
Cross is still alive.
[LENALEE exhales]
The one thing that
remains to be seen
is whether the Innocence he's
carrying really is the Heart.
Whatever the case may be,
we need to locate him
as soon as we can.
You know,
I've helped the Order from
the shadows for years.
I'm happy to finally work
alongside Exorcists.
It's an honor, and well,
I'm happy for the opportunity
to be closer to my love.
You really miss him.
[ANITA] Uh... Please pretend
you didn't hear that.
Even if it's true, a supporter
speaking that way
about an Exorcist
is inappropriate.
Not at all.
It's fine. You'll see him soon.
[YANG]
Come on! You're holding us up!
The longer you take,
the longer we stay docked!
That's Allen and the others.
[LAVI sighs] They're dead set
on making us earn our passage.
[KRORY]
The keyword here is dead.
[LAVI] [ALLEN] [KRORY]
Exorcist or human, the more
deckhands we have helping
the quicker we can leave,
don't you agree?
[ALLEN]
I see your point, but still.
[LENALEE]
Thanks for your hard work!
Oh. Lenalee.
Hold on, Allen. Let me
see your left arm.
Oh man! Why's it crumbling?
Even I find that morbid.
Stop worrying! I'm fine.
I promise, it looks
worse than it is, guys.
I've been fighting a lot lately
and I guess my weapon
finally got tired.
It just needs a little
rest, that's all.
This is the first time
I've heard of a weapon
getting exhausted.
Maybe 'cuz I'm a Parasite
Type Exorcist?
You're just making
up excuses now!
Whatever the reason,
it is true that you're
fighting twice as much
as we are, thanks to
that eye of yours.
[LENALEE] It's not a
laughing matter, Allen.
This is exactly what
I was afraid of.
Your left arm is fragile.
[gasps]
There's no need for that.
[LAVI]
Look. Allen made her cry.
[BOOKMAN]
He sure did.
Seems to happen a lot.
[ALLEN]
I-I didn't mean to!
[LENALEE whimpers]
We set sail!
You heard the lady!
Let's get moving!
[CREW]
Yeah!
Hey, Timcanpy.
You think we can find my
Master once we cross the ocean?
He has no idea the effort
everyone is putting into
finding him.
Not that he'd care.
If it turns out you're dead,
I'll never forgive you.
[ALLEN gasps]
Akuma?
Uh...
Somewhere in the distance.
You see something?!
[ALLEN grunts]
There!
Heads up!
We've got company!
[ANITA gasping]
[LENALEE gasps]
I've never seen
this many before!
[MAHOJA]
To your battle stations!
All hands! Prepare to attack!
The Akuma wasted no time
deciding to halt our progress.
There's not enough of 'em.
What do you say, Krory?
You hungry?
My teeth are aching.
[ALL]
Innocence... Activate!
[ALLEN yells]
[MAHOJA, ANITA grunt]
[LAVI gasps]
[BOOKMAN]
Hm?
Why are they flying
past the ship?
[LAVI] They're just ignoring us?
What gives?
[LAVI] Who the hell
do they think they are,
running from a fight?
[ALLEN]
What's going on?
Any theories behind this?
It's unclear, but it seems we're
not their intended target.
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN]
Wherever they're headed,
we can't let them reach
their destination!
[AKUMA A]
Just as I suspected.
I knew they were Exorcists!
You can tell by the black coats.
A dead giveaway.
No one's got better
vision than you!
[AKUMA A]
Watch it!
[AKUMA B]
Whoa!
Man, they're fast!
Hang on, Allen! I'm coming!
[AKUMA C]
This ship is full of Exorcists!
[AKUMA D]
What'd you say?
[AKUMA E]
Not only that,
it's filled with humans
ripe for the picking!
So hard to choose
who to kill first!
[AKUMA groan]
[ANITA]
Don't underestimate us!
[AKUMA E]
Pathetic worms!
You're only buying
time with your barrier.
It won't keep Levels
Twos out for long!
[ANITA grunts]
[AKUMA F]
You left yourself exposed.
--[MAHOJA grunts]
--[AKUMA F whimpers]
[MAHOJA]
No one threatens my master!
[AKUMA F]
Why you...
[AKUMA E]
You bastards!
[ANITA]
Uh!
[MAHOJA gasps]
[AKUMA E]
We're gonna crush you!
[LENALEE screams]
[groaning]
[AKUMA D groans]
[AKUMA G yelps]
[LAVI] If you want to crush
someone, take my advice.
Next time, do it like this!
[AKUMA E groans]
Thank you! You saved our lives!
Let's not congratulate
ourselves just yet.
[BOTH gasp]
[AKUMA H]
A ship crawling with Exorcists!
[AKUMA I]
And look! Humans, too!
On the bright side,
I can attack with my eye closed
and hit a target every time.
True. I didn't think
the dining on this ship
would be this generous.
Get ready!
[ALLEN gasps]
He thinks he's faster
than you! What a laugh!
How's that Exorcist?
Good luck catching me!
[ALLEN grunts]
[LAVI] Summon Devouring Flame!
Fire Stamp!
[AKUMA A]
Damn! That was close!
[KRORY grunting]
Ha, ha!
Heaven Compass!
[AKUMA scream]
[AKUMA M gasps]
[AKUMA M]
Damn it! Put me down!
[LENALEE]
Waltz. Misty Wind!
Are you badly injured?
I'll make it.
That's good to hear.
Timcanpy? Where's Allen?
Allen...?
[ALLEN gasping]
[yelps]
They got him!
[AKUMA N roars]
[LENALEE yells]
[LAVI] Lenalee! You have
to rescue Allen!
[BOOKMAN] You're the only one
who can catch up to the Akuma.
Use your Dark Boots
and bring him back.
[KRORY] There's more than enough
of us to protect the ship.
What about--
[ANITA]
Please go to him.
[LENALEE]
Anita...
Capable as he is,
it isn't safe for Allen
to be fighting alone.
He may be an Exorcist,
but taking on that many Akuma
without help will overwhelm him.
[LENALEE]
Uh.
Don't forget, we're Supporters
of the Black Order.
Everyone aboard will fight.
Leave these Akuma to us.
I understand.
[KRORY]
Hurry.
[LENALEE]
Got it.
[ALLEN grunts]
[AKUMA A] What good is it going
to do you shooting other guys?
You know, if you really
want off this ride
you ought to do
something about me.
Then again, are you sure
you really want to?
I mean if you blast me
I'll drop you.
You'll plunge hundreds of feet
to your inevitable demise.
[ALLEN groaning]
[AKUMA B grunts]
He stepped on my head!
The Exorcist stepped on me!
[AKUMA B screams]
[AKUMA A] How dare you!
I won't let you get away!
[ALLEN groans]
Not even a scratch...
[yelps]
[AKUMA O] You sure we
should be doing this?
[AKUMA A]
Meaning what?
[AKUMA O] You know I love
capturing Exorcists,
but that's not the
job we were given.
If we don't hurry up with
the Millennium Earl's orders,
won't he pulverize us?
[ALLEN]
What job?
[AKUMA A]
Oh come on, relax.
You're just jealous 'cuz I
get to kill the Exorcist,
aren't you?
[AKUMA O]
Ha, ha! Yeah, kind of.
Give me the right
half of his body.
[AKUMA P] That's not fair!
Save me a piece or two!
[ALLEN]
What's this job they mentioned?
It's possible there's
Innocence located nearby.
But still, sending such a large
number of Akuma is unusual.
[ALLEN yelps]
[AKUMA A]
Did I break your concentration?
This is no time for daydreaming!
[ALLEN grunts]
[AKUMA A]
Hows this?
With your left
arm in my mouth,
it makes it difficult to
do much of anything, huh?
Ha, ha! I'm not gonna
drop you, little one.
You're mine to kill.
[LENALEE yells]
[AKUMA A]
Close one!
Lenalee?
I demand you let
Allen Walker go!
[AKUMA A]
No chance girlie!
The only way you're
getting him back
is if you can take him from me!
[LENALEE]
Innocence, Level Two!
Release! Barden!
[AKUMA growling]
[LENALEE] Sounds are vibrations
that travel through the air.
The Sound Shackles turn those
vibrations into footholds,
allowing the wielder
to move at sonic speed!
[AKUMA A]
What the...?
[LENALEE]
Take this!
[ALLEN screams]
Allen grab my hand!
Lenalee!
[gasps]
[ALLEN gasps]
[AKUMA Q]
Here we go!
[growling]
What am I looking at?
[LAVI yells]
[LAVI] This feeling...
Something's wrong.
[KRORY grunts]
I sense it as well.
It's on the other side
of those mountains.
And we're stuck here,
with the worst possible view.
[roaring]
[AKUMA R]
Forward!
[AKUMA S]
Bring it down!
[AKUMA growl]
[LENALEE]
Ahh! Sound Shackles!
Whoa. You're quick on your feet.
Sorry. Are you okay Allen?
Yeah. I'm all right.
But, more importantly...
[ALLEN gasps]
[roaring]
Why are they attacking it?
Their job. Is that
what they meant?
Their goal was to
destroy this thing?
[roaring]
[gasps] His face...
It's Suman.
Once again... A Fallen One.
[LENALEE screams]
What? Why did you scream?
Are you hurt?
He's a Fallen one.
[gasps]
[LENALEE] Someone who failed
to become an apostle.
[ALLEN]
Suman Dark.
An Apostle of God who failed.
After being taken inside of him
I learn the shocking truth.
On the next D. Gray-Man :
"Fallen One." Bring salvation
to this poor Akuma's soul.
Starting today we have a new
on-going segment that, uh...