[screeching]
What are those?
[SUMAN] It seems that...
my life is coming to an end.
I'll soon be dead,
and when I die,
I'll take this monster with me.
It'll die, too.
I'm sorry. I only wanted
to see my family.
I'm so deeply sorry.
[ALLEN whimpering]
Stop it! Leave him alone!
[ALLEN grunts]
I said get off him!
[ALLEN grunting]
[ALLEN]
You bastards...
[ALLEN groaning]
[ALLEN]
Stop!
[ALLEN cries]
Teez. Enough.
[ALLEN gasps]
[TYKI]
Heh.
Come here.
[ALLEN gasps]
[TYKI chuckles]
My, my. Look how much
bigger they've grown.
[ALLEN gasping]
[ALLEN]
Wait a minute. I know him.
He's from Suman's memory!
[ALLEN gasping]
[ALLEN]
I can't take it!
I wanna live. I beg you.
And what might your
name be, good sir?
[ALLEN gasping]
[ALLEN]
You're a Noah.
You're gonna pay!
[ALLEN gasps, groaning]
[TYKI]
Huh?
[TYKI] The boy's left arm.
It must be his Innocence.
In any case, why does
he look so familiar?
[TYKI gasps]
[ALLEN chuckles]
Now I remember!
From the train! You're the
card shark that cheated us!
I guess I can't blame you for
not recognizing me in this form.
[ALLEN]
Tell me. What did you do?
[TYKI]
Pardon?
[ALLEN]
To Suman. Is he dead?
You killed him.
Isn't that right?
Answer me!
You would have done the
same thing in my shoes.
He was the enemy.
[ALLEN growls]
[TYKI]
Well.
I guess there's no harm in
telling you about my ability.
It's not like you can run
and give any of your
friends the details,
but you'll only hear it once. So
perk those ears up. Understood?
[ALLEN whimpering]
[TYKI]
These guys are called "Teez".
Basically, they're
man-eating Golems
created by the Millennium Earl.
The butterfly shape was
his idea. A personal touch.
All you need to know is
that they feed on humans.
And the more they eat,
the more they grow and multiply.
However, that's their
ability. Not mine.
I don't want you to
get the wrong idea.
I just use the Teez as a tool.
On the other hand,
my power... is this.
[ALLEN grunts]
[TYKI chuckles]
Don't look so worried.
You won't feel any pain.
Impressive, huh?
My hand, actually
my entire body,
can pass through
anything I choose.
But that's only one half of
my ability. 'Cause you see,
when I want to touch something,
it's a different story.
Say I pull my hand through
and decide to grab a
part on the way out.
Some vital organ.
Your heart for instance.
I could remove it
from your chest,
still warm and pumping blood.
No problem.
Wouldn't even require cutting
your body open with a knife
to pluck it out.
[ALLEN grunts]
[TYKI] Imagine having
your heart extracted
while you're still alive.
[heartbeats]
[TYKI] What do you think
that would feel like?
Come on.
Why don't you tell me?
Are you afraid to die, boy?
Uh?
[TYKI gasps]
What a killjoy.
I wasn't really
going to take it.
If I did, I'd only get my
gloves stained with blood.
Normally I'd let
the Teez feed on you,
or it'd be a waste
to have them on hand.
[ALLEN]
Normally?
Yes. You mean you haven't heard?
About your dead comrades
who were found
with their internal
organs missing?
[ALLEN gasps]
[TYKI] Daisya Barry.
Kazarna Rido. Charcar Lavong.
As for Suman,
since he helped me,
I gave him special treatment.
I decided to make his
body into a nursery
by planting Teez inside of it.
Seems it was effective.
Look at how much they've grown.
[ALLEN grunting]
Come to think of it,
I also encountered a
General named Yeagar.
[ALLEN gasps]
[TYKI]
If I remember correctly,
I didn't kill him
outright either.
Damn it. There was a
reason. What was it?
[ALLEN]
General Yeagar...
[TYKI]
Oh, that's right!
I used him as a
messenger instead.
I gather he was in
quite a bit of pain
by the time you found him,
seeing as his insides
were mostly eaten.
How... How dare you.
[TYKI]
Huh?
I'm sorry. What's that?
You killed them.
Oh, I see! They really
didn't tell you, huh?
[ALLEN grunts]
I won't forgive you!
[TYKI]
I confess,
I didn't think you had
this much fight left in you.
No matter. In your state,
you won't hold out for long.
[snap]
[ALLEN screams]
[ALLEN groaning]
[TYKI] Regrettably,
you caught me at a bad time.
I'd hoped to meet you
again in my light form.
Then perhaps I would
have challenged you
to a game of cards instead.
[TYKI] But this is my dark
side, and at the moment
I'm busy killing people
associated with
a certain individual.
Perhaps you know him.
So tell me, boy. Your name
wouldn't be Allen Walker?
[LENALEE]
I'm close.
Suman's light disappeared
around here.
[LENALEE]
Come on, Allen.
[LENALEE] You should be here.
Why can't I find you?
[LENALEE]
Allen! Answer me!
[LENALEE] I have to hurry.
But where are you?
[LENALEE] What is this?
This awful feeling?
Allen...
[ALLEN]
This isn't good.
The condition my body's in...
I can't even stand,
let alone fight.
If only I was stronger.
Why am I weak?
[ALLEN groaning]
[TYKI] Answer me. Your name
is Allen Walker, yes?
[CELL RORON]
You got the right victim, sir.
Yes. No doubt.
Allen Walker.
[CELL RORON]
Delete him.
[TYKI] I don't think
you've been introduced.
This is Cell Roron,
prisoner of the List Cage.
It's his responsibility to point
you out when our paths cross.
[ALLEN screams]
Now that I've found you,
I think I'll start by getting
rid of that Innocence of yours.
[TYKI]
Didn't you know?
Innocence isn't impervious.
It can be destroyed.
At least in the hands
of the Clan of Noah
or the Millennium Earl.
This can't be real.
[TYKI]
Every time we kill an Exorcist,
we collect their Innocence
and proceed to eliminate it.
Once we destroy the Heart,
all Innocence,
no matter how far away,
will shatter and
disappear forever.
It's quite dramatic, but that's
how we know we have the heart.
I wonder,
could yours be the one the
Earl's been searching for?
How about an experiment?
That's Suman's Innocence
beside you, right?
So if it disappears after
I destroy yours, then,
that would mean your Innocence
was the Heart all along.
Since you like to gamble,
would you care to wager
who has better odds?
[TYKI chuckles]
Don't do it.
Don't destroy it.
[ALLEN]
Didn't you hear me?
Don't do it!
[TYKI laughs]
[gasps]
[ALLEN gasping]
[TYKI] Now. Let's see
if that was the Heart.
[TYKI]
Well, shoot. I guess it wasn't.
We'll find it.
Besides, my job right now
is assassinating
people on this list.
[CELL RORON]
Delete him! Delete him!
[TYKI]
Yeah, yeah. Enough. I get it.
[CELL RORON]
Sorry.
[ALLEN]
Listen to me, Tim.
I need you to take Suman's
Innocence and run.
You can't stay.
You have to.
[ALLEN]
There's no other choice.
If you stay here, who's going
to help them find my master?
Now, go.
It's up to you.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Thanks for everything, Tim.
[TYKI] Well, I guess that
was a wise decision.
[TYKI]
Akuma. Go after it.
[AKUMA A grunts]
[AKUMA A] Hey, everyone.
We got new orders.
The Noah wants us to
capture that Golem.
[AKUMA B]
You're crazy if you think
we're going to disobey the Earl.
[TYKI]
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but he gave you explicit orders
to recover the Innocence
from the Fallen One.
[AKUMA B]
Did you hear that?
[AKUMA C]
It's the Noah's voice.
[TYKI] The golden Golem has the
Innocence in its possession.
I'm a little
preoccupied right now,
so you find it and
take the credit.
[AKUMA cheer]
[AKUMA B]
What a great guy!
[AKUMA C]
Let's go!
[AKUMA A] The golden
Golem is good as dead!
Did you see that? Just now.
Some kind of flash trailing
across the sky.
[KRORY]
I did. But what on earth was it?
The morning greets
us with ill omens.
A red dawn means blood
has been spilled.
[LENALEE]
Lavi! I need your help!
[TYKI] I bet I can guess what
was going through your head.
You realized it's hopeless.
You thought, "might as well send
this Golem to my comrades".
But I'm afraid
you've shown your hand.
You're prepared to die.
[ALLEN]
It isn't hopeless.
[TYKI]
Hm?
[ALLEN] As long as Tim
makes it back to the Order,
hope will never fade away.
[TYKI] An optimist right until
the very end, aren't you?
Well, you can pray to
your God that happens.
You could ask for anything.
But at some point, you will have
to face the harsh reality.
Your God isn't here. Only me.
[TYKI]
Teez, do me a favor.
Don't devour this one.
Just puncture a little hole
in his heart instead.
A quick death would be a
disservice to such a brave soul.
Let's give him time to reflect
on his life before he dies.
Long enough for the blood
to spill out of his heart,
and for the fear to
wash over his body.
Slowly writhing in pain,
until eventually he dies!
[ALLEN groans]
[gags]
[BOOKMAN]
Hm?
It can't be!
[TYKI] Did it hurt a little
more than you thought?
Sorry, but look on the bright
side. Your suffering's over.
[TYKI]
Huh?
Sweet dreams, boy.
Forever.
[ALLEN]
The moon...
Even down here it looks so big.
[ALLEN]
I'm not ready.
Don't come for me.
I'm alive. Still alive.
[ALLEN]
Not yet.
[FO]
Dammit.
I can't see anything through
this. What's with all the fog?
[FO grunts, yelps]
[FO yells]
[FO]
Ouch! My nose broke the fall!
Uhh!
Why the hell are these
scattered all over the forest?!
Uh.
Looks like a Karuta card.
Someone lost their deck.
Where did it come from?
Uh!
This isn't good.
Looks like I'm too late.
[LENALEE]
While awaiting Allen's return,
a messenger from
the Asian Branch
delivers the news of his fate.
Further pushing us towards
the abyss of despair.
Will we ever emerge?
And will we ever move on?
On the next D. Gray-Man :
"Loss and Reunion."