This is hardly the
time to take a break!
We have to keep moving.
Right.
Did you locate Daisya?
No... Not yet.
His Golem was transmitting
a weak signal earlier...
Maybe it gave out.
Maybe.
Daisya can look after himself.
He's bound to be
here by morning.
All right...
I'll start heading
your way, too.
My patience has run out...
I've seen that skin color...
And I've seen those
scars...! Are you...
One of the Clan of Noah?
And what if I said yes?
Charity Bell...! Activate!
Ohhh... That was scary.
If you liked that,
then you'll really
get a kick out of this!
How clever.
Well, I guess that's
the end of that...
But how did you--?
You're referring
to your end, right?
I'm really going
to enjoy killing you!
What...? Daisya...?
Is that you?
Daisya no!
Whatever you're gonna do...
Do it.
That was faster than I expected.
If you have any last
requests, now's the time.
There's nothing...
Just do it.
Very well.
At least... I was never bored.
If I don't watch my step,
I could lose my other life.
I can't let that happen.
I must admit...
Having both a light
and a dark side...
Is quite thrilling...
Who would have thought?
That's Daisya's Golem all right.
We've received instructions
to have his body transported
to the Order along
with the Finders.
And the Akuma?
We've successfully
driven every one
of them from the city...
There are still a few
outside the south border,
but we're keeping
an eye on them.
We can't just leave them
and hope they'll
go away on their own.
Besides, the General is
still out there somewhere.
There's only one
thing we can do.
Yeah.
Look after Daisya.
I was expecting more.
It is him!
At least there won't be
much cleaning up afterwards.
I call on the Maker
of Eden... Activate!
And acknowledge all the beauty
that there is in this world.
Art!
Wait, what's he doing?
Is that an anti-Akuma weapon?
General!
Kanda...! How long has it been?
Poor boy...
Daisya deserved
better than that.
May he rest in peace.
He was always a good kid...
Even when he used to break my
glasses with his Charity Bell,
I knew he had such
a gift for doing good!
His body is scheduled to be
shipped to Headquarters today.
The Order also took his
Charity Bell for safekeeping...
We're escorting the body...
Marie and I would be honored if
you would join us on the trip.
If my memory serves me,
Daisya came from the
town of Bodrum, didn't he?
Huh...? Oh...
That's right.
It's a breathtaking
little village
on the edge of the Aegean Sea.
General...
We believe the enemy is
after you for your Innocence,
and they'll stop at
nothing until they get it.
I haven't seen the Bodrum
shoreline in many years,
so this sketch
may not be accurate.
Daisya...
May your hometown find
you and bring you comfort,
no matter where you are...
Goodbye, my dear old friend.
I won't be traveling with you.
I'm a General of the Order,
and a General can't walk off
the battlefield in
the middle of a war...
And besides...
It's my duty to find
and train new Exorcists.
If God hasn't already
given up on us...
we should be on the lookout in
case he sends more disciples.
I knew he'd say
something like that.
Some people never
change, do they?
General Tiedoll.
We're coming with you.
Oh no!
Allen...! Lenalee!
Yeah, hello...
Is Devon around?
It can't be...
No!
Yes, I understand.
We'll contact you again soon.
Chief...
That was a call
from the unit in Spain.
It seems the battle in
Barcelona is finally over.
And the General?
As far as we know,
General Tiedoll is safe...
And the Akuma force has
been driven from the city.
Excellent.
However--
Many units sustained
heavy casualties...
And there's more.
Units in other regions are
reporting losses as well.
We have no choice...
All we can do is wait and
have faith in our people.
That's strange...
How did I end up here?
What's this?
I guess I must have taken
a wrong turn somewhere...
I'll have to ask
someone for directions.
Do you think we got them all?
Yeah.
Those monsters gave us more
trouble than I expected.
If we don't find General Socolo
soon, it might be too late.
Right.
From the Tiedoll Unit,
Daisya Barry.
From Socolo Unit...
Kazarna Rido...
and Charcar Lavong.
From Klaud Unit...
Tina Spark, Gwen Frere,
and Sol Galen.
All told...
Six Exorcists gave
their lives in battle.
Including Finders,
that brings the number
of confirmed dead...
to one hundred and forty eight.
I can't believe we've lost
so many of our members...
And for six Exorcists to
fall in a single battle...
It's completely unheard of...!
For apostles of God,
they didn't last very long.
If they couldn't
stand up to the enemy,
what chance do the
rest of us have...?
It's only a matter of time.
The Millennium Earl...
Do you think he'll kill us all?
I've heard enough.
A hundred and forty-eight
soldiers died to keep you safe.
They deserve more
than your whining...
Welcome home.
You will not be forgotten.
So, the same cause of
death as General Yeager?
That's right...
The autopsies showed that
the bodies of three Exorcists
were in the exact same
condition as the General's.
Daisya, Barry, and both
men from the Socalo Unit...
Rido and Lavong.
Although there are no visible
openings on the bodies,
each of them has had one of
their organs completely removed.
That can only mean...
The Clan of Noah.
Both the Socalo
and Tiedoll Units
were three-man teams, leaving
three Exorcists who survived...
Do we have reports
on their status?
Kanda and Marie from Tiedoll
Unit returned unharmed...
That much has
been confirmed... But--
The third member of Socalo
Unit is still missing...
Suman Dark.
That is surprising.
Chief Komui!
What is it?
We'd like permission to go
to our Leader's hometown,
so we can give his
remains to his family.
And you are?
I'm one of the members
of the Arias Unit...
We were attacked
by a swarm of Akuma
in a mountain pass as we
were traveling to India.
Our leader sacrificed himself
to make sure the rest
of us got out alive...
Before he died...
He told me he had a son back
home who would be about my age.
I'm begging you...
Let us take our leader home!
The deceased are to be cremated
and buried here
on the grounds...
The Black Order has
been perfectly clear.
There are no exceptions.
Contacting the families of
the deceased is forbidden...
Any information about
members of the Order,
living or dead,
is strictly classified.
What about their families?
They died trying to
make the world safe,
you can't just
forget about them!
Can you give me
your word that those
in your unit who died
won't be turned into Akuma?
Or that your Leader's son won't
do absolutely anything to bring
his dead father back to life?
Their last mission in protecting
the world is to
vanish altogether.
There's too much at stake.
I can't afford to
be sentimental...
I have to stay
focused on victory.
Hello you two...
General Tiedoll!
Yes, it's me...
Come on, it'll be morning soon.
There's no doubt
this city has seen
some devastating things
over these last few days.
Yes...
I only wish that Allen and
I could have gotten here sooner.
We came as fast as we could,
but by the time
we reached the city,
the battle was already over.
It was hopeless...
We might as well
have stayed home
for all the good it did...
God knows how many
people we could have saved,
if we had just
gotten here earlier.
General...
The Order needs your help...
Will you be going back?
As long as I'm able
to serve the Order,
I'll continue in my own way...
Right now that means
finding more Accommodators
of Innocence...
Each of you has
responsibilities of your own,
but you know that...
The battle may be over,
but the war isn't...
There've been four
Generals attacked so far...
So it's a safe bet who
their next target will be.
It's so obvious!
My Master?
That's right...
And I hope for his sake that
you find him before they do.
Right.
But I don't imagine
he'll be too pleased
about the idea of suddenly
having two Exorcist bodyguards.
Yeah... Good point.
But General Cross doesn't
have to worry about it,
because we don't have
any clue where he is.
That shouldn't be too hard...
I thought everyone
knew about this.
Within Timcanpy--and every
Golem--is a feature that
allows it to sense the
person that created it.
Okay...
Tell us where we
can find General Cross.
He stopped moving.
It looks like he's facing east.
Nothing's gained by
dwelling on lost battles...
The war against the Millennium
Earl is just beginning.
Yes, sir.
Right.
Be careful General Tiedoll...
Goodbye...
We'll see you again someday!
I thought they'd never leave.
That boy is nothing but trouble.
That's true...
But from this point on--
The path set out before
them is fraught
with dangers the likes of
which they've never imagined.
There's not a doubt in my mind.
Speaking of new journeys,
it's time we started ours.
Right.
Anything you say, Master.
As far as the eye can see, red
roses dominate the landscape.
After the losses we've suffered,
they do wonders to
soothe our aching hearts.
On the next episode of
D. Gray-man: "Requiem Roses."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!