Right! Let's get going!
Chaozii! Move!
What happened?
Say something, Allen!
[CHAOZII shudders]
[ALLEN gasps]
Who are you? Tyki?
But that's impossible.
I destroyed your Noah.
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN]
Where'd he go?
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN] Not only is he
powerful, he's fast too!
I can't even counterattack!
Is this thing really a human?
[TYKI yells]
[ALLEN]
No!
Tyki Mikk...
Who are you?
What did you become?
[TYKI yells]
[TYKI growls]
Is that Tyki Mikk? And what's
with his outfit? Is this a joke?
Lavi...
Just hang in there, Allen.
Hold on to me and
we'll get out of here.
We can't escape. The door...
It doesn't exist anymore.
[LAVI]
No way.
It was destroyed?
Then, there's no way
for us to leave the Ark.
[TYKI laughs]
[LAVI gasps]
[TYKI grunts]
[TYKI laughs]
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI]
Extend!
[TYKI growls]
[LENALEE] Allen!
Are you all right?
[LAVI] Dammit!
What do we do now?
Say something!
[LAVI] Both Allen and I
are complete wrecks.
We can't fight. And there's
no way out! But...
There's no choice but
to get to higher ground!
[LAVI, LENALEE gasp]
[TYKI growls]
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI grunts]
[TYKI growls]
[LAVI]
I can't hold him off!
[LAVI] Devouring Flame.
Direct Fire Stamp!
[LAVI groans]
[LAVI] No, it can't be.
Not like this.
Lavi! No!
There's no way...
Is this the same Tyki
from earlier?
The Noah? But I thought
Allen already defeated him!
[TYKI growls]
[LAVI pants]
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN grunts]
[LAVI]
Not good!
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN yells, grunts]
[LAVI] He's too strong.
There's no way we can stop him!
You can't give up!
[CHAOZII]
We're so close!
I'm sorry. We're never
getting out of this place.
The door was destroyed.
[LENALEE gasps]
I saw it. His first attack
shattered it. We're stuck.
[CHAOZII]
That can't be!
[ALLEN screams]
[LAVI growls]
Lavi!
But we're doomed!
Why are you still fighting?
Simple.
We're Exorcists, Chaozii.
[LAVI yells]
[LAVI groans]
Lavi!
No. You're only going
to injure yourself more!
I have to fight
with Lavi and Allen!
But we're defeated,
so what does it even matter?
Because I'm an Exorcist too,
and we never give up!
[CHAOZII gasps]
I don't understand
them. I can't!
[LENALEE]
No!
[LENALEE gasps]
Le... Lenalee...
[CHAOZII gasps]
[LENALEE] Is this the end?
Am I going to die?
Without saving anyone?
[CHAOZII]
Get up, dammit. Get up!
I'm so useless!
I'm sorry, Anita... Mahoja...
I'm too weak.
I can't do anything.
Why am I not strong
enough to help?
Forgive me, Anita.
I can't save them! Forgive me!
[ANITA] Rain. This was
Cross's favorite weather.
[MAHOJA] Master. The work
is finished as you asked.
What are your orders?
[ANITA]
Stop the ship!
Go summon the Exorcists and
Akuma to join us on the deck!
So that's it.
Kie and Maosa.
Out of the crew, you're the
only ones who survived.
[KIE gasps]
[KIE, MAOSA grunt]
[MAHOJA] What is it?
Speak up, you two.
[KIE]
It's just that...
[MAOSA]
There's another...
[ANITA]
Mm?
[MAOSA] But he's
being kinda stubborn.
Dead! I'm as dead as
the rest of you, ya got it?
No, you're not.
Definitely a lie.
I know for a fact you
didn't get shot, Chaozii.
You're wrong! I did!
Accept the truth.
It's time someone
told you, Chaozii.
You're not a very good liar.
Everyone here
knows you survived.
I am telling you the truth!
I got hit, all right?
[CREW MEMBER]
Then look her in the eyes
and repeat what you said.
[CHAOZII gasps]
Crewman Chaozii Han.
I'm sorry, Captain Anita.
Please let me go
down with the ship!
Beside you and
the rest of the crew!
I forbid it.
We mean so much to you,
but you're okay lying to us?
[CHAOZII]
This place... Edo...
It's full of Akuma.
Isn't that right?
If I go, a normal human like me
is sure to wind up dead anyway.
Even if by some slim
chance I did survive,
I'd be lost without Anita
and the rest of you.
I don't have a reason to live
or anywhere to go back to!
My home...
It's with you guys!
When my mother was
killed by an Akuma,
it was you and your
mother who delivered me!
The only reason I'm alive
and aboard this ship right now
is because of you two!
I chose to support the Order
and devote the remainder
of my life in your service
to repay the debt I owe you!
And if fate has decided you
should sink into the ocean,
then that will be
my fate as well!
I beg you to grant me
this one request!
Please let me stay with you!
[CHAOZII sobs]
[ANITA] It requires
greater courage to live.
Believe me, I understand
exactly how you feel.
But you know, Chaozii, nothing
ever really disappears forever.
Even if our bodies are
swallowed by the sea,
our life force will join
you and the Exorcists.
We'll be right beside you
to help carry on the fight.
And together, we can
continue to save more lives.
You see, whatever battles
the future holds, even though
you won't see us standing
next to you, we will be there.
Reaching out to you
from the ether.
You must go on.
Live though this for me.
Though we won't see
each other anymore,
we'll always be friends.
[CHAOZII weeps]
[ANITA]
I have only one thing to ask.
Use your life to protect
those young Exorcists.
As long as you do that,
I promise you...
We will never leave your side.
[LENALEE gasps]
[CHAOZII]
I failed you, Anita. Everyone.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I can't do anything!
[LENALEE gasps]
[TYKI growls]
[CHAOZII yells]
[CHAOZII yelps]
[CHAOZII]
The tower!
[LENALEE grunts]
[LENALEE yells]
I got you, Lenalee!
[CHAOZII] Can you hear me,
Anita? Mahoja? My comrades!
[CHAOZII gasps]
This is for you!
Help me save her!
[TYKI laughs]
[CHAOZII grunts]
Oh, Chaozii...
[LENALEE gasps]
[LENALEE] It can't be!
That's Innocence!
And it appears to be
reacting to Chaozii!
But what's its source?
Where is it coming from?
Go. You know I won't
try to stop you.
[CHAOZII grunts]
I know you're with me, Anita
and Mahoja! For my friends!
It's amazing.
[CHAOZII grunts]
Who are you?
Report!
So reinforcements
are being sent.
I don't recall hearing
about additional guards.
Wait while I confirm this.
[CHAOZII grunts]
Hold on!
[LENALEE grunts]
[LENALEE] What's this
binding wrapped around me?
I can't break free!
[CHAOZII yells]
What's happening?
How am I doing this, Lenalee?
There must be Innocence nearby
you're somehow
synchronizing with.
You can't keep this up.
It's the same as Miranda.
His body's carrying
an incredible burden.
It may be an
Equipment Type Innocence.
The Innocence you're reacting to
is in a raw crystallized form!
It hasn't been weaponized yet!
An accommodator can't
wield that kind of power!
If you keep this up,
you'll be injured!
Too bad! I mean,
what else can I do?
If this how it ends,
then so be it!
[CHAOZII groans]
[CHAOZII grunts]
[CHAOZII yells]
Chaozii, no...
Miss Anita!
Mahoja! My shipmates!
[CHAOZII screams]
[CHAOZII grunts]
[LENALEE] You're pushing
yourself too hard!
[CHAOZII] I can't
overdo it at this point!
I either hold up the
wreckage or I let it fall!
I don't mind the pain. I finally
got the chance to save you!
Hurry up! Before I let go,
you need to run! Right now!
Where would I run?
The door leading out is gone.
[CHAOZII grunts]
But still... I won't give up.
I refuse!
I'll never give up!
And neither will I!
[CHAOZII grunts]
[TYKI chuckles]
Not this guy!
[TYKI yells]
[CHAOZII grunts]
[LENALEE]
Big brother!
[TYKI yells]
[TYKI growls]
[LENALEE gasps]
[CHAOZII gasps]
[CHAOZII, LENALEE laugh]
It's Allen!
And Lavi!
[LAVI pants]
[ALLEN pants]
Lenalee sounded
kinda surprised
both of us are
still in this fight.
I have to admit, I'm a
little surprised myself.
I didn't think I had
any energy left.
That makes two of us.
With the door gone and no way
to get out, it'd be easy to
lie down and just give up.
[ALLEN] Then again,
when have you and I
ever thrown in the towel?
That's true. If Chaozii and
Lenalee won't back down...
Then we can't lose hope either.
[TYKI grunts]
[LAVI, ALLEN yell]
[TYKI yells]
[ALLEN, LAVI yell]
Allen's hit!
Lavi!
He got both of them!
He's behind you!
What?
[TYKI growls]
[ALLEN]
Clown Belt activate!
Getting confused?
[TYKI growls]
I'm the one you're
supposed to be fighting.
That's why you're here,
isn't it? For me.
I'm the one you
want to kill, right?
[TYKI growls]
Watch out, Allen!
[ALLEN grunts]
Getting careless, or did
you forget? I'm still here!
[TYKI grunts]
[LAVI yells]
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN grunts]
Is that it? We may not
get out of here alive,
and this may be my last battle.
But I'll keep fighting
until my final breath!
[TYKI yells]
That's the promise
I made with Mana!
[CHAOZII, LENALEE groan]
No!
[TYKI laughs]
[ALLEN screams]
[ALLEN] Our fierce battle
with the transformed
Tyki Mikk continues.
As we're backed into a
corner, and all seems lost,
an Exorcist in hiding
makes his appearance.
On the next D.Gray-man,
"Judgment."
Bring forth salvation
to this poor Akuma's soul!
[TYKI laughs]
[LENALEE laughs]
[LENALEE]
Huh?
What's the matter, Lenalee?
A mosquito, I think.
Ah.
[TYKI groans]