You're the one to blame!
No... I...
I can't believe you saved me!
Do you really have to cry?
You'd cry too if the
landlord just saved your life!
When I woke up here,
I was tied up.
And the next thing
I knew, he was--
You mean you were
asleep the whole time?
That's right...
I was having this beautiful
dream about a steak!
Wait... is this
the Witch's Cabin?
Don't ask me.
I don't even know
how I got here!
You came here all by yourself?
I don't remember anybody else.
But I don't think I'd remember
even if somebody was there,
with the way I was dreaming.
I can see it now--the biggest,
juiciest steak there ever was!
I kept trying to eat it,
but whenever I got close
the plate ran away from me!
When I came to,
I was all alone and
tied up in this bed.
I guess... that's
not too helpful, is it?
Oops...
You're disgusting.
All this excitement
is making me hungry.
I'm glad I still have these
jellybeans from earlier.
Oh, no!
There's a hole in
the bottom of the bag!
I must have been dropping
beans the whole way here.
I thought you left
that trail on purpose!
And waste all
that delicious candy?
No sir, not me!
If it wasn't for Sofia,
I might have been in trouble!
So now what?
Now that you know the danger
involved, what will you do?
Me...? Probably
go back to my room
and eat the rest of the
jellybeans...
Wrong...
We're not done here.
Hold on...
Do you see the path
just beyond those trees?
It leads out of the village.
Since we're already so close,
maybe you should
think about leaving!
In fact, I should join
you so you don't get lost!
Why's that?
You have to help me!
I'm begging you...!
Please believe me...
There's a witch
living in this town!
We have to get out of here!
Please!
We're staying.
No...
Listen... Pull yourself
together...
Where is the witch?
By the looks of the cabin,
someone had been living
there until very recently...
Where are they now...?
Why won't you answer me?
Are you protecting the witch?
What was that?
What scared the
landlord so bad...?
Kanda...? Why did
he run off like that?
It seems there truly
is a witch in town.
What?
I'm glad you stuck around...
Akuma.
I'm sorry!
Please sir, try to hang
on as long as you can.
I'm sorry...
Please forgive me!
It's time to go.
Okay.
Sofia.
I'm glad you came back.
Where have you two been?
When I woke up my father
and both of you were gone,
I was so worried.
Well, the... the
thing is, you're dad...
Sofia...
I have bad news.
Do you?
I'm afraid your father is dead.
He was killed by an Akuma while
trying to escape the village.
That is bad news.
Sofia...
You're the witch, aren't you?
Kanda...! The poor thing
just lost her father!
Will you please shut up...?
Answer my questions.
Are you the witch that plagues
this village or aren't you?
I'm not...
You're mistaken.
I see.
Then who has been living in
the Witch's Cabin until now?
For generations this town
has told the legend of a witch.
And for years, any old
woman unfortunate enough
to live alone in
Dankern Village was cast
in the role by the townspeople.
The role?
Yes.
In return for small daily
meals and a place to stay,
she took on the scorn and
hatred of the entire town.
She became their witch.
As long as there
was someone to blame
for all of the town's
troubles and misfortunes,
the people felt safe...
And as long as they felt safe,
the legend of the
witch survived.
No way...
But one month ago...
The old woman who was
the town's witch, died.
But... old people
die all the time, right?
It just happens.
Idiot.
The legend is
important to them...
If the village witch is dead,
she has to be
replaced with another.
Correct.
They just couldn't stand
to break the tradition...
They needed a witch
as soon as possible...
And it wasn't long before they
had selected her replacement.
It was Angela...
They choose my sister...
A little girl?
Yes...
She was actually my twin...
However...
Unlike me, Angela was
weak, and in poor health.
Hey, Angela.
I thought...
Maybe I could stay here.
What's so funny?
That certainly isn't the way
you were talking yesterday...
You went on and on about how
you wanted to see a city...
Does that sound familiar?
I'm glad I finished in time.
What's this?
I want you to take extra
good care of yourself
when you're in Mitterwald.
How long did it
take you to make it?
You know how much
you need your rest!
How else are you
going to get better?
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's just...
You never think
about yourself...
You always do so much for me
and I never get to do
anything for my twin sister.
I didn't mean to upset you.
Oh, Angela!
I promise you...
I'm going to find
a way to fix this.
I'll come up with the money
for your medicine somehow,
and we'll get a
doctor to look at you!
You'll be healthy
one day, I swear it.
And when you are,
we'll never have to worry
about anything else again.
I know...
Thank you.
But...
As soon as I started
working in Mitterwald;
Angela was chosen
as the next witch.
Father tried to stop them,
but no one would listen.
They took Angela
out of her sickbed
and moved her to the
cabin at the edge of town.
And that's where she stayed.
All alone, with no
one to look after her,
in that cold, dark cabin.
It wasn't long until
she fell into a coma.
She held on as
best as she could.
But in less than ten days...
I died.
It can't be...
That's so sad!
You said "I."
The day after I died...
Angela came back...
hoping to save me.
My body was still
lying on the bed
in the Witch's Cabin,
when she found me...
"My body"...? Whatta...
What are you talking about?
It's simple... You see--
That was when Sofia
met the Millennium Earl.
She wha--?!
That's right.
Angela!
This is my fault!
I'm sorry...
If I'd only been there--
Oh...
I hate to see a pretty girl cry.
But just because fate
deals you a bad hand,
it doesn't mean
you have to play it.
You can still have
your sister back.
Take revenge on God for
what he's done to you...
Show 'em you're in
control of your own destiny!
Now doesn't that
sound wonderful...
You could do that...?
Bring her back?
Of course!
You only have to wish for it.
Sofia... My god...
What have you done?
Angela...
Welcome home!
Yes...
Now you can be together at last!
All that remains is
for you to destroy her!
We never have to be
apart, ever again.
Angela!
Sofia.
I won't ever leave you.
Now... Let's begin.
Poor thing...
That's terrible...!
The two innocent little girls
had to lose their lives...
Just so the
townspeople could keep
their stupid fairy tale alive!
How nice of you to say that.
But there's really no
reason for you to cry.
Sweet boy...
Don't you understand...
I chose to bring myself back...
You see--
It was my decision
alone to cheat death...
I sacrificed my own
life in order to gain
one that couldn't
be lost so easily.
Then Sofia and Angela...
The twin souls that
longed to be together
combined to create
a powerful Akuma.
Does that mean the villagers--
It does!
No way...
Are they all Akuma, too?
I think you're right...
You turned everybody
in town into an Akuma?
That's... That's like
something a real witch would do!
That's exactly right.
I saw the legend
appealed to people,
so I made it real.
How could you?
How could I what?
Your father...
He loved you.
My father's only responsibility
was to watch over this town.
But instead he
chose to run away.
This is his fault.
He tried.
How dare you pity him...?
He was a pathetic old man...
Because of him--
You're wrong!
I don't feel sorry for your
poor father and what you did...
The one I pity is you.
You're even dumber
than I thought...
Save your pity...
It's wasted on me!
If you're finished,
I'd like to continue...
Oh really... What a
wonderful idea...
Goodbye, Exorcist.
What are we gonna do?
Dankern belongs to its witch...
And every unfortunate soul
who crosses these borders
must suffer at her hands!
No one leaves
this village alive!
Get back...
You'll only get in the way...
Find a place to hide.
Unless you wanna die.
Right!
Idiot!
This is the end.
You're not suited
to be a Finder.
Kanda!
This is bad!
If the virus gets
into your body through
any of those wounds, you'll...
You don't have
to worry about me.
What if we can't stop
the virus from spreading?
My body isn't affected
by the Akuma virus.
Just forget it.
But, you're hurt!
I'll be fine.
Innocence... activate!
Bring forth calamity!
Netherworld Creature...
Ichigen!
There's one thing
I neglected to tell you.
What is it?
The last words your father
spoke before he passed away.
"I'm sorry...
Please forgive me."
So?
They were the same last words
as the villager I had
defeated before him...
"I'm sorry,
please forgive me"...
Who could they have
been apologizing to?
Who knows?
And who cares?
I have far better things
to concern myself with.
I suppose you have a point.
Oh, good...
I'm glad we see eye-to-eye.
You must have killed
thousands to reach this level.
And I've only just begun.
Not if I can help it!
Burn in hell.
No...
This is my room!
But how...? It's impossible...
How did she do it?
Impossible...
Yes...
It is impossible.
Prepare to die.
After you.
How?
You can read the memories
of your opponent...
You show him his
greatest desire in the form
of a dream in order to
distract and confuse him.
You weren't affected...
I showed you your true desire,
yet you're still calm.
The memory that you showed me...
That was only the surface
of my heart's one true desire.
You saw the lotus wither,
but you don't
understand its meaning.
Or what I long for.
My true desire can't
be granted by another,
no matter how powerful...
How dark...
And curious...
I never would have imagined
you were so complicated.
Sofia!
Oh no...
Stay back!
I'm evil...
I know you are...
But I still don't
want you to die.
Come back, Sofia!
Crying over a witch...
You're ridiculous...
Over... a witch.
I couldn't do
anything to help her.
It hurts so much!
Sofia...
Angela.
There is another Exorcist--a
clumsy bean-sprout of a boy--
who says he can see
the souls of Akuma.
I've heard.
According to him,
whenever Innocence is used
to release a soul from
the body of an Akuma,
that soul flies away to
heaven to live forever in peace.
Yeah...? Is that really true?
So... You're saying
not only are Angela
and Sofia's souls
finally together...
but they got to go
to heaven, as well?
Who knows...?
I was just telling you
what the kid told me...
Believe it if you want.
Akuma are Akuma.
Wait!
Where are you going?
There's nothing more
for me to do here.
Time to move on.
Well hold on a second!
Wait for me!
Quit following me.
I told you, you're not
suited to be a Finder.
Go back home.
But who do you have
to help you dress
all those fresh wounds?
They've healed.
Healed?
What do you mean, "healed"?
It's how my body works.
Don't worry about it.
I finally completed
my mission...
I wasn't able to retrieve
any Innocence, but...
all the Akuma in the
area were defeated...
All by yourself?
No...
It was Kanda...
I helped when I could,
but he did most of the work.
Wha...
Kanda...
Yeah...
That guy is one
incredible Exorcist...
My hero.
You certainly took
your time getting here.
What's wrong, Kanda?
You act like things
are finally looking up.
Which means?
Only that the
better your life is,
the more you seem to sulk.
I've known you long
enough to see it, my friend.
Whaddya say...?
Did I hit the mark?
Deep inside the forest,
a vicious pack of wolves
begins to attack the
townsfolk living there...
And the one who appeared before
them was none other than--
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"Exorcist Clad in Wind."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!