It always belonged to me...
I was wrong, I shouldn't
have run away.
But... just that once...
I did... and now...
Aren't we there yet...?
Come on, guys...
I'm really starving here.
Yeah...
I feel you, Allen...
I'm tired, too...
and I'm thirsty,
I'd give anything for a drink!
I know...
Hang in there, everyone...
I think we should be
getting close to a town...
Lavi...! Is that a...?
Yes...! We did it...
It looks like we're actually
headed to a real town!
Finally!
Man o man, they gotta have
something to drink here!
Yes, food, here I come...
I'm so glad!
We've been saved!
What's this?
We made it!
Yeah...!
Hey, wait...
This is strange...
Where are the people?
I wonder what's going on?
Do you think maybe...
it's a ghost town?
It can't be a ghost
town, I'm thirsty.
How am I gonna get a
drink if no people are here?!
There's something
wrong with this place.
As far as I can tell,
there are waterways
running in all directions inside
the perimeter of the town.
And yet...
They all seem to be empty.
What does that mean?
It means the water's dried up.
Forgive me for
interrupting--are you travelers?
Oh, fantastic...
Sorry, it's just nice to know
that there are
people in this town!
I realize it's not much but...
under the circumstances
it's the best I can offer...
Please... it's great!
It's wonderful, seriously...
Well then, go ahead and dig in.
Thank you very much!
Your people seem to
be suffering here...
Well, it's not easy...
We've all been
scrambling ever since
the town's water
source started drying up.
The source?
That's right...
You see there's a
good-sized lake
located just a short
distance outside of town.
It held plenty of water
that naturally overflowed
and fed directly
into our waterways...
However, about a
month ago the water level
started dropping
lower and lower,
and we can't for the
life of us figure out why.
It's gotten so serious
we had to start rationing
our drinking water.
Have you discovered
why this is happening?
No... we still don't
know the cause...
According to all the people
who've been watching
the lake and investigating,
even after a heavy rain
the water level there
keeps decreasing.
Wait a minute... after
a rain the level's down?
How can that be?
It's certainly...
a mysterious phenomenon.
Indeed... one worth
looking into.
Good point...
Would it be alright
if we took a look
at the water
source as well...?
We might be able to find
some overlooked clues
that could help out...
Go ahead...
If you wanna get to
the lake from here...
just go out the front gate
and hang a hard right...
then keep going straight ahead
and you'll
eventually run into it...
If you can help us in any way,
we'd all be very grateful.
Well, we'll do our best, sir!
What...?!
Why do Lenalee and I have
to stay here in town?!
Come on...
Even if we check the
lake that doesn't mean
we'll be able to
solve the mystery.
It makes sense that
someone should stay behind
to question the townspeople,
especially about what was going
on around here a month ago...
and with Lenalee
growing up in China
and all I figured it'd be
easier for her to talk to 'em.
Okay, sure!
But I... I just wanna--
If we find that Innocence
is causing the phenomena
there are likely other
things present as well.
Akuma!
Bingo...!
And now that that's settled
we'll leave the investigation
of the town in
your capable hands.
Let us know if you
come up with anything!
Don't worry--we will!
You guys be careful!
C'mon, Lenalee,
I'm always careful!
Okay, let's find
someone to talk to.
He was right.
This isn't much water at all.
How strange, no wonder the
town's waterways are dried up.
Do you see something, Bookman?
Seems the
water's still receding.
Look at that...
How could the level go down
when the town
isn't drawing off of it?
Could something
have happened to it?
Well, it's possible
the lake water
could be draining or
disappearing somewhere.
But what would cause
something like that?
If it isn't flowing out anywhere
then I'm guessing there must be
something actually in the water.
I see!
Then let's jump in...
we can take a quick dip
and see what's in there!
No, wait!
Is something the matter?
What's going on here?
I think they're the townspeople.
They must've decided the lake
water needed to be guarded.
Due to the fact they're losing
their only water source...
Concern on their part
is easily understood...
I'm afraid if we dove
into the lake right now
while they're watching we'd
invite an unpleasant scene.
Then, how will we be able
to discover the
cause and help them?
We'll still check it out,
because the sun's
gonna go down eventually
and it'll be a lot easier to
get around them in the dark.
That's a great plan!
Yes, we have no
choice but to wait it out.
They're Exorcists.
We have to get our hands
on it before they do.
Our mission is to kill all
the miserable Exorcists.
We should do it tonight!
Yes, as soon as possible!
What...?
Fortune teller?
That's right...
The story around town
was that the fortune teller
could see anyone's future
by using a crystal ball...
But then, about a month
ago they suddenly stopped
telling the fortunes
and no one knew why.
That's about the time
the water started drying up.
Would you mind telling me
where their house is, ma'am?
There... end of the street.
Well that's interesting...
I know...
How'd it go for you?
I circled around and got
a good look at the town,
but I haven't seen any
signs of Akuma anywhere yet.
That's good...
Well then let's go
see what we can learn
from this fortune
teller, shall we?
Hello...? Is anyone home?
Hello?
Maybe they went out for a bit.
Who are you?!
What did you come here for?
Well... you see, sir...
We're doing some investigating
and heard that you stopped
telling people's fortunes
around the same time the
water started drying up.
How dare you... Get out!
And don't come back!
But sir, wait!
Please, just tell us why
you stopped seeing people.
I have nothing to say to you.
But any information
you have, could help us!
I said no...! Now leave!
Grandfather...
We're worried about the
town's water supply, sir...
If you would only--
Who's that?
Get out of here!
Leave me alone...!
I have nothing to say to anyone!
I guess he doesn't want to talk.
Grandfather, what were
those people doing here?
Don't worry about
them, Mei Ling...
I don't imagine they'll
be coming back here soon.
But I... I saw her...
I think she's the
one in my vision...
You must, forget about it.
I see... alright.
We'll keep
investigating the town...
Be careful.
I can't believe they didn't
find out anything, either.
But they've still got
tonight to investigate
the lake and you and
I'll just have to be ready
to work a little
harder tomorrow.
Let's do it!
It's almost time!
Well well... they're still here.
I can't wait to see
the Exorcists in pain.
I think I'll go find the girl...
Then I'll wait here.
Is there something
wrong, old man?
You can investigate
the lake without me.
Say what?
I'm going back to town...
I'm counting on you.
Hey... wait, what's goin' on?!
Find her... find her...
Must... find her...
There she is!
Who's there?
Please open the door... hurry!
Oh, it's you!
I'm sorry it's late,
but I saw you today and
I knew I had to find you.
It's no problem...
I'm glad you're here ...
Come in!
So, Mei Ling, is the fortune
teller your grandfather...?
Are you okay?
Yes, but...
I'm the one who
tells the fortunes.
I'm so sorry...
It's just... I assumed...
You gotta understand
my grandfather's
just really worried about me
and that's why he was mean
and drove you away like that.
It's alright, we're fine...
Why did you decide to come
here tonight and talk to us?
Um, well...
Because...
I'm... I'm worried
about the town
and, and the
water's almost gone.
Before, I really liked
it when I could
make the people happy by
telling them their fortunes...
But now... it's just awful...
Everyone's suffering so much.
Oh, I see...
I bet you can
tell what's going on...
is that it?
No... I can't...
Hey... you did say you're a
fortune teller, didn't you?
Uh, yes...
Miss Lenalee.
Just "Lenalee," okay?
Yes, Lenalee.
I have an idea...
If you have the ability
to actually look
into people's futures,
then maybe you could try
to see the reason
the water's drying up.
I... I'm not able to
tell fortunes anymore.
Why?
The only way
I can discern any part
of the future is
by using my crystal ball
and I can't now because
Grandfather and I threw it away.
Oh no...! Where is it?
We threw it into the lake
a-a-about a month ago.
Are... you sure about that...?
You did it a month ago?
Yes.
Well then... maybe...
it's the crystal ball...
Wow.
But if it's your ball,
does that mean
it contains Innocence?
Innocence?
Yeah... it's an object that
has very special powers...
Mei Ling?
Yes?
What made you throw
the crystal ball away?
Why would you want to do that?
Because...
We did it... because
we thought that...
I didn't mean to
do anything wrong!
Hey, everything's
going to be okay, really!
Lenalee, the Akuma!
What is that thing?!
Hide!
I want you to stay here...
Don't go anywhere!
Noooo!!!
What's wrong?
No!!!
Mei Ling, come back!
Stop!
Lenalee!
There you are...
The little fortune teller girl.
Who... Who are you?
So nice to meet you and
now you're coming with me!
Mei Ling?
Akuma!
What took you so long, Exorcist?
You're not goin' anywhere!
Oh really?
Lenalee, get outta there!
Thanks, Allen!
No...! Mei Ling!
Mei Ling... Mei Ling?
Where are you...? Mei Ling?
Who's there?!
You have nothing
to fear from me,
but I must ask you a
very important question.
What's that?
That was intense, wasn't it?!
A few more seconds
and we would've been
sucked into that thing.
Yeah, could you
tell what it was?
I don't have any idea...
The water looked like
it was disappearing
as it was being
sucked into that light.
Lavi...
Ah crap...
Here we go again...
You ready to fight?
Of course!
This sucks!
Die!
Mei Ling was taken by an Akuma
and was about to be swallowed
up by the surface of the lake
when, at that very
moment, a great light
began to shine from
beneath the water...
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"Wavering Accommodator."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul!