Road, stop it, Lero, stop!
I think I'm gonna be sick!
No way!
I'm having too much
fun to stop now!
But that's exactly my point!
This is no time
to be having fun!
The Earl is going to
punish us as soon as
he finds out you took
me without permission!
And you know how
I hate being spanked!
Would you stop
worrying, Lero...?
I told you, he won't scold us!
Oh boy...
This last day's been fun...
He's such a joy to fight.
This town is perfect.
Its people are
well-off and peaceful.
This seems to be a happy
and successful village...
They are excellent specimens
for creating faithful Akuma.
I miss you so much!
But timing is everything,
when a happy human
has been plunged
into the depths of sadness...
I will come.
Good evening Miss.
You no longer need
to cry my child...
I can bring your husband back
from that detestable God.
I will call back your husband's
soul to its rightful place,
but first you must
do something for me...
From the depths of your
heart, call out to him.
My love...
Come back to me!!!
No... my love...
Is that really you?!
What...? How could
you do this...?
You turned me into an Akuma!!
Now you will
follow this order...
Kill your wife and wear
her body as your own.
Komui?
You're finally awake...
How are you feeling?
I've been a lot better...
So tell me...
Is Lenalee doing alright?
She's fine...
It's certainly nothing
to worry about.
I'm glad she's doing well...
What type of treatment
is she receiving?
It's called acupuncture...
It's a Chinese therapy
that uses needles in the
skin to relieve pain.
Sounds painful.
You can give it a try
if you'd like to...
What...? No way!
Can I ask you a question?
Please do.
Okay...
Why did you choose to
come all the way out here
when you have so much
work to do back home...?
Of course you
care for Lenalee,
but you're here
for something else.
What can you tell me
about the Noah family?
He came here to ask
me that same question.
What's he doing here?
I didn't even see him come in.
The Noah family has
had great influence
for generations but
you'd never know it...
And their power has never
been officially recorded...
Yet, somehow they've
always popped up
at the major turning
points in history.
They've appeared once again
and have taken the
side of the Earl...
That's the reason why
your Chief came here.
To speak with the Bookmen,
who are the only known living
humans to have knowledge--
Talk is cheap...
Still don't know when to
keep your mouth shut, eh...?
How many times must I say it?
The Bookmen's information
can't be divulged to outsiders.
What's he doing here?
Where are all these
people coming from?
Easy...
I don't see the big deal...
I mean you're getting up
there in years grandpa,
so I'll be replacing
you soon anyway.
You fool...!
Only you could be naïve enough
to think you're worthy
of filling my shoes.
You crusty old panda.
Oww!
You old coot!
Allen Walker.
The prophecy speaks of you as
being the Destroyer of Time.
Yes...
That's right.
On behalf of all the Bookmen,
it is an honor to meet you...
Bookmen?
We investigate
secrets in history
that aren't part of official
record and make them official.
Let me tell ya, a lot
of hard work goes into...
Oww...!
That hurt!
Shut your mouth!
We are currently acting as
Exorcists with special duties.
I don't have a typical name...
So just call me Bookman.
Oh, okay.
Now that is very strange...
It appears as if
your left eye has
begun to regenerate
of its own volition...
I suppose my needle treatment
won't be necessary after all.
I guess that means
I'm pretty lucky...
I heard it's a
curse of some kind.
Yes... it is...
I injured it as a boy when I
turned my father into an Akuma.
You should probably
lie down and get some rest...
When Miss Lenalee
awakens you'll need
to report for an
assignment immediately...
So be ready.
Tell me, how did it go?
Just fine...
He said treatment
wouldn't even be necessary.
That's good...
You could probably
use a bit of fresh air.
So why don't we take a walk?
Woah!
Sounds like they're having some
sort of festival, doesn't it?
Yeah.
So how old are you?
About fifteen.
Ah, I'm older than you...
I'm eighteen.
Fifteen, huh?
I guess it's just your gray hair
that makes you look older.
My hair?
So, Lavi's my name, but
people call me Junior...?
What's your nickname...?
What about "Short Stack"
sound alright kid?
Well that is what Yu
referred to you as.
Yu?
Oh wait...
So you don't know...?
That's Kanda's first name...
It caught me off guard too...
Strange huh?
I didn't know that...
I thought he just went by Kanda.
Next time you run into him...
you should call him Yu
and see if you can get a
good reaction out of him.
Of course you probably won't
see him for quite a while...
I have a feeling
that our assignments
are only gonna get longer and
more difficult as time goes on.
Really?
Why do you say that?
The Noah family appearing
is proof enough for me...
It most likely means the Earl is
stepping up his operations...
We'll have to play again soon.
And next time we'll let the Lord
Millennium set the stage for us!
Well that's the reality
of the situation so we
need to be ready...
Damn him...
I became an Exorcist
for one reason.
To destroy Akuma...
not to murder my
fellow human beings.
Hey... Hold on...
You okay...? What's
wrong, Short Stack?
My name's Allen!
I'm going ahead on my own.
I'll meet up with you later.
Whew...
It's just a joke...
I need to wrap my head
around this Noah family...
Why are they
working with The Earl?
Feels nice, doesn't it?
This is how it's supposed to
feel when two humans embrace.
What's going on?
I feel scared...
What am I afraid of...?
Is it the idea of
being around humans?
Any one of them
could be Akuma...
Without my left eye,
I'm useless...
There's no way I'm able to
tell Akumas from humans...
I might as well be blind!
Want some flowers...?
You should smell them,
they're fantastic.
They're really pretty...
Mister Exorcist.
Now die... Exorcist scum!
That sure was a close one...
gotta be careful, Short Stack...
Lavi.
Who else would it be?
Y'know it's way too dangerous
to be out on these
streets by yourself.
Ah great!
Look out!
It's a monster!
Big Hammer Little Hammer...
Grow, grow, GROW!
It's huge!
Keep your head down!
Take this!
He destroyed the whole building!
The nerve of those Akuma playing
ball in the street like that.
Come on...
Let's get outta
here while we can...
The street is the worst place
to be to get stuck in a battle.
Um, right.
Ready...? Now hold on.
Okay.
Big hammer, little hammer...!
Extend!
Who the hell are they?
Police...!
Someone get the police!
That is every single trace
of information I have
on the Noah family
in my records.
This will be a huge help to us.
Thank you, Bookman...
I'm sorry all this took so long.
I really appreciate it.
Well, of course...
I'm only doing my job.
I know how stressful this
must be for you, Chief Komui...
The presence of Akuma
alone is troubling enough...
but the addition
of the Noah family
will complicate
things even further.
It's not so bad...
Those who really have
it hard are the Exorcists.
But, me...?
All I do is send
them into battles
to do the dirty work while
I stay back at headquarters.
Everyone's in pain...
In times of war, suffering
is what brings us all together.
Hey, are you gonna
throw up, Short Stack...?
Y'alright?
It's Allen!
That weapon is incredible...
I can't believe it can fly, too!
I know...
I couldn't live without it.
Doesn't it get heavy...?
Especially when
it fully extends?
Not at all...
It stays the same weight
no matter what its size.
Wow.
So uh... what in the
heck is wrong with you?
Huh?
Back in town,
why did you wait until they
transformed to attack?
That'll get you killed quick...!
You know?
Yeah.
I take it your left eye
can detect Akuma
and it's not working.
Then you have to do this
just assume every human
you come across is a bad guy.
But that doesn't work...
Because only a small amount
of humans are actually Akuma.
Sure you can say that...
But here's the thing...
I can see you're afraid
of humans... right?
You feel defenseless without
the use of your eye...
Now you're noticing how exposed
you are with normal sight.
I'm afraid, you might be right.
Look here...
You can't afford to trust
anyone until your eyes fixed...
Because any of those
people could be an Akuma.
It's a threat that we're forced
to deal with every single day.
So then what do you
usually do to deal with it?
I pretty much assume every human
is an Akuma and I trust no one.
For most Exorcists,
we're all at a huge
disadvantage...
We're not like you with
your all-seeing eye.
Unfortunately, Akuma easily
blend in with humans...
There's no way
for us to distinguish
between friend and foe
when we're in a crowd.
This is the case for pretty
much all of us Exorcists...
We see humans as allies to
the Earl in one way or another.
Hold on.
You're wrong...
You can't just kill everyone
because you don't trust them.
That's true...
Good point...
That's why I wear this coat.
Huh?
This coat draws the
Akuma closer to me.
There he is!
It's him!
He's so handsome.
He really stands out
in a crowd, doesn't he?
Master...
I don't understand...
Why do you have that coat?
You're attracting a
lot of attention.
Foolish apprentice...
Because I'm different
from you, you idiot.
Huh?
Master...!
This is exactly what
I was afraid of earlier...!
Now we're surrounded
because of that coat!
What's the problem with that?
I don't see any point in trying
to hide from your enemy,
when your enemy is invisible...
This coat is a target
and by wearing it I can suspect
anyone who approaches me.
Hey, what's wrong?
Lavi.
Hm?
Aren't you always
afraid though...
being the target of
Akuma wherever you go?
To be perfectly honest
I'm more afraid of humans...
because someone I'm good
friends with today...
could be an Akuma tomorrow.
It happened recently...
A guy I knew turned
into an Akuma...
He and I had actually been
close, personal friends
for some time.
Don't get me wrong...
it drives me nuts...
But listen...
What other choice do I have?
Destroying the Akuma
I come across keeps me alive,
then so be it.
You must be prepared to
make yourself a target...
in order to protect the
humans around you...
Are you capable of
handling that...? Allen?
He's over there!
Where?
Yes, those are the ones.
Get your hands up...! Right now!
You...
You're coming with me.
Wait, uh... What'd we do?
That's enough outta you, kid!
He's an Exorcist...!
He's mine...
Watch out!
We're outmanned!
Yeah...! I know!
Big Hammer Little Hammer...!
Grow...! Grow...
Grow!
Come on...! You need
to be quicker than that!
Right...
I will!
It makes sense now...
All Exorcists, including
Lavi and Master Cross,
must see humans as the enemy,
just like I'm having
to do right now.
By using themselves
as a decoy in order
to draw in the Akuma,
they use the best ways
they're capable of to protect
the innocent people around them.
It's a completely
different way of fighting.
Hey, nice shot.
I've been a poor excuse
for an apprentice...
How could I just now be
understanding Master's guidance,
years after he taught it to me?
I wonder...
if you even have
that fear... Allen.
I finally get what he meant
when he spoke of the fear.
If my left eye
can ease any fears
among my fellow Exorcists
while I fight alongside
them in battle...
If I can provide
just that one luxury...
Yeah...! We got 'em!
Please...
Please, somebody help me!
Help me, Please!
Thank you so much!
Are you hurt?
Nice try.
Not bad, kid.
Thanks.
Looks like your eye healed up.
Wow, that was fast, huh?
Woah, it's snowing!
Check it out!
Can you believe it?
See Allen...? Look!
Hey, you!
C'mere!!
Come back here!!
Hahahaha...
I'm gonna get ya!!
I'm gonna get ya...!
I made the decision
to take this path...
the path of an Exorcist...
I need to be prepared...
and I need this coat.
Far gone lies a town that
suffers from turbulent weather.
One moment there's a blizzard,
and the next a heat wave.
Kanda, Lavi and
myself are traveling
to this village to
face a dangerous threat.
On the next D. Gray-man:
"The Leaf of Revival."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.