♪
[KANDA]
Mugen, Activate!
Nigen Swords!
Come. Time is short.
[LERO]
Lero, Lero, Lero.
Yu.
We have to press on.
Yeah.
Kanda.
[SKINN] You made a grave
mistake when you crossed
Skinn Bolic of the Noah Clan!
Who are you, anyway?
I know you're from Tiedoll's
Unit, but what's your name?
Kanda.
[SKINN] I like sweets.
Do you enjoy them too?
[chuckles]
Actually, I hate them.
[SKINN growls]
[KANDA grunts]
[grunts]
[SKINN growls]
[SKINN grunts]
[SKINN chuckles]
[gasps]
[SKINN shouts]
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN] I'll never forgive.
I'll never forgive.
Never forgive. Never forgive.
Never forgive. Never forgive!
[SKINN yells]
[ROAD] Then I heard
a loud voice saying,
"Go. Pour out the seven bowls
of God's wrath on the earth."
The first bowl was poured out,
and ugly, festering sores broke
out on the people who
had the mark of the beast
and worshiped its image.
The second, and the sea
turned to blood like that of a
dead person, and every
living thing in it died.
The third was poured out,
and the rivers and springs
of water became blood.
The fourth, and the sun
scorched people with fire.
The fifth, and the
beast's kingdom
was plunged into darkness.
People gnawed their tongues
in agony and cursed God.
The sixth, and the great
river Euphrates was dried up.
Then I saw three impure spirits.
They came out of the mouth of
the dragon, and of the beast,
and of the false prophet.
Last, there came flashes
of lightning, peals of thunder,
and the earth quaked.
And the cities of
the nations collapsed."
[SKINN growls]
Never forgive.
I'll never forgive
you Exorcists!
[SKINN]
Never!
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN grunts]
[SKINN]
Thunder!
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN shouts]
[KANDA]
Over here.
Mantis Slicer!
[SKINN grunts]
[grunts]
[KANDA gasps]
[SKINN grunts]
Ouch.
How about that?
You're faster than me.
[KANDA] He can still stand up?
But that was a direct hit.
It seems to have had some
effect, but even Nigen isn't
powerful enough
to take him down.
How can a living being
be stronger than Akuma?
The Noahs are powerful.
Well, no matter.
[gasps]
[SKINN]
Hm?
[KANDA] Another quake.
It won't be much longer now.
[KANDA]
Nigen. Sublimate!
[SKINN]
Huh?
[KANDA] Starting now, this blade
will increase its owner's power
at the cost of his life!
[KOMUI]
You're not immortal, Kanda.
You have to remember that.
[KOMUI]
Your life is still finite.
Be careful not to
miscalculate it.
In exchange for my life,
grant me strength!
Engage, the Sangen Style!
[SKINN grunts] Pulling out
the big guns already?
You must be in a hurry!
Heh. I didn't decide to stay
in here and fight with you
just for the fun of it.
If that's what you want, you can
have fun in the underworld!
Underworld, huh?
You should know by now,
if I'm going there, then I'll
be taking you with me!
Especially since
you're using that.
It may only be burning
your hands right now,
but you'll be a dead
man soon enough!
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN]
You're dealing with Skinn Bolic!
I am the Noah who spreads anger!
My body contains every ounce of
the rage and resentment that the
Noah Family's been
building up for years
and releases it as millions
of volts of deadly energy!
Don't you get it? Every time
you cut into me with those
blades of yours, you're only
inflicting that energy
onto your own body! You're
making this so easy for me!
Mankind incurred God's wrath!
And they'll be punished
by burning to ashes!
[KANDA]
Say what you want.
I'm going to live.
[SKINN shouts]
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH grunting]
[SKINN groans]
[SKINN]
How can that be?
That damn human's
even faster now!
[SKINN] My eyes aren't
quick enough to keep up
with all his movements. Still...
[SKINN growls]
[SKINN shouts]
[SKINN] The more you attack
me and dilute my power...
[SKINN] ...the more
you destroy yourself!
[SKINN] You're about to
lose this fight, Exorcist.
I'm gonna kill you, and you're
gonna help me do it!
[SKINN laughs]
You should be careful too.
You're laughing because
you're sure you'll win.
But you're leaving me so many
openings I almost feel guilty.
[SKINN groans]
[SKINN] What the hell?
I don't understand.
When did you get a chance to
c-cut me this many times?
Well, either way. You may have
just done a lot of damage to
my body with those weapons,
but the fact that you did
means that you don't
have much life left!
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN] Just as I thought.
Those poor hands of yours
are barely holding on,
aren't they?
[laughs]
[KANDA groans]
[KANDA] Sangen Style doesn't
just drain away my life energy,
it also causes me to
not recover as quickly.
[KANDA] But in order
for me to finish him off...
[SKINN] Alright, perfect.
That should do it.
You've cut me enough times now.
[SKINN laughs]
[KANDA gasps]
[SKINN]
The tank's all full!
[KANDA groans, shouts]
You tried your hardest.
Isn't that sweet?
And it just so happens.
I love sweets!
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN]
Thunder!
[KANDA shouts]
[KANDA grunts]
Well, don't say
I didn't warn you.
I told you before, the more you
hack and slash at me like that,
the more those weapons
conduct my energy straight
into your body to kill
you from the inside out.
What do you think these chains
are that I hold in my hands?
They're made out of
the anger of the Noahs
that's about to tear you apart!
So tell me. How does it feel
being attacked from inside
your own body, you pathetic
Exorcist trash?
[SKINN]
Divine Punishment!
Aw, come on.
You're not gonna die
this soon, are you?
[gasps]
He's alive? It can't be!
I told you. I won't die.
In fact, I can't die.
These chains are annoying.
I'll just have to
slice them to pieces!
[SKINN]
Waste of time.
Those chains can
never be cut by anything.
[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN]
Looks like it's all over.
You might be quicker on your
feet than I am, but I think we
both know I'm a hell of a
lot more powerful than you.
You don't have the slightest
chance of making it
out of this room alive.
Swordplay is all about
distance between
you and your opponent.
But you can't control your
distance with my chains
swinging around
you like a whip,
so those swords are as
good as twigs against me!
[SKINN] It's the end
of the line, Exorcist.
You've lost this battle.
Now, suffer and
cower at my feet.
Go ahead! Nothing eases my
anger better than an agonized
expression on the face of one
of you worthless Exorcists.
[KANDA]
[SKINN growls]
[SKINN] What? Why does he
still look so determined?
Isn't he afraid to die?
[SKINN]
Hey! Aren't you afraid to die?
[KOMUI]
Kanda, aren't you afraid to die?
[KANDA] I'm not going to die.
My wounds have healed too.
You're healing slower. Don't you
understand that's a problem?
Not if I still can heal.
[KOMUI] You don't seem to
realize how serious this is!
It means that... your body
is starting to fall apart.
Kanda. You only have so much
left. Do not overestimate it.
[KANDA grunts]
[KANDA]
No. I won't die.
[SKINN]
Dammit. Give up!
[KANDA gasps] It looks like the
room's about to collapse.
[SKINN]
Huh? Not long now.
The room's gonna
disappear soon.
[LENALEE gasps]
Oh, no!
Part of the ark
must be crumbling!
[ALL gasp]
[LENALEE]
Kanda.
[KANDA] I don't have much
time before it all vanishes.
I'd better hurry
and finish this.
[KANDA gasps]
[SKINN] Huh? Well, the way
we came in is gone.
It looks like all
that's left is the exit.
[SKINN]
So, you or me?
Who do you think's gonna get
out of here in one piece?
Not both of us.
I told you already.
[SKINN]
Huh?
[KANDA] I'm Kanda,
you oversized spark plug.
[KANDA] I'll be the
one to live, not you.
[SKINN]
Keep dreaming!
[KANDA grunts]
[chouts]
[SKINN shouts]
[KANDA grunts]
--[SKINN shouts]
--[KANDA grunts]
[SKINN]
I'm not done yet!
Divine Punishment!
[KANDA shouts]
[SKINN]
Still not done!
[KANDA]
I won't.
[SKINN] Not done, not done,
not done, not done, not done,
not done, not done!
[KANDA]
I am not going to die.
Not yet. I can't die.
Someone needs me.
[SKINN] Thunder, thunder,
thunder, thunder, thunderbolt!
[SKINN growls]
[SKINN]
Hey.
What's your problem? You oughta
be long dead by now.
[MIRANDA gasps]
[BOOKMAN]
What's wrong?
[MIRANDA]
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
[BOOKMAN] Miranda. Did something
happen to them up on the Ark?
No, they're okay. Thanks to my
abilities, I'm carrying the
timelines of everyone who's
trapped up there right now.
None of those timelines have
disappeared from my sight
so far, and if one did.
I would know about it.
I promise you,
that all of our comrades
are definitely still alive.
[grunts]
[KANDA]
I... I... I...
[SKINN] Hm? How many times
do I have to kill you?
Just drop dead!
[SKINN]
Guess I'll have to separate
your head from your neck!
[groans]
[SKINN]
Huh? What the hell?
I was waiting for
the right moment.
[SKINN yells]
[KANDA grunts]
Hurry up and die!
[SKINN yells]
[KANDA shouts]
[SKINN groans]
[SKINN coughs]
[SKINN gasps]
[SKINN] Innocence. I feel
it taking over my body!
How could this happen to me?
Don't tell me. You kept
withstanding my attacks
until your weapon began to
melt so it wouldn't take any
more of your life energy?
But... You can't use your
Innocence anymore either.
It's worthless to you now.
Noahs never die, huh?
That is absurd.
Who started that rumor?
[KANDA] You're still a
human being, aren't you?
And no human is immortal.
[heartbeat]
[SKINN]
Noahs are immortal.
♪
[ALLEN] It seemed like
the battle with Skinn Bolic
had come to an end.
However, Skinn's undying hatred
for Innocence enables him
to keep moving and continue his
fight against the Exorcists.
On the next D. Gray-Man:
"Noah's Memory".
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
[ALLEN]
A mysterious student
just transferred to
D. Gray Academy.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[LENALEE]
Huh...? A new kid?
Why am I wearing these clothes?
[ALLEN]
To be continued?