[ALLEN] I don't know what's
wrong with me either.
Uh.
[ALLEN]
I mean, do you think I want
to be stuck here doing nothing?
I don't know what to do!
How long?!
How long do I have
to keep doing this?
The reason you feel
so compelled to fight
is because you have something
important to protect.
Something important, huh?
That's right.
[ALLEN] Because I have to
protect what's important to me.
[FO grunting]
[ALLEN grunting]
[yells]
[yelling]
[ALLEN grunting]
[LO FWA gasping]
Amazing!
[yells]
[gasps]
[FO] Seems like he's
really fired up today.
[FO yells]
[FO]
And yet...
...his Innocence refuses to
return to its physical form.
[ALLEN]
Dammit.
[BOTH grunt]
There's got to be a
logical explanation.
[LO FWA, LI KEI]
Huh?
Do you remember when Walker
first began the training?
His Innocence held
physical form.
His concentration's
improved since then.
Yet, there's less
materialization.
It's strange.
And these past couple of days
there hasn't been any at all.
[LI KEI] You'd think
there'd be a correlation.
If his mind is sharper, the
revival time should increase.
What on earth do you
think it means?
Innocence refuses
to follow logic.
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN]
What's wrong with me?
Hey Fo.
You should stop being
so hard on yourself.
Yeah. But I just...
Part of me feels like I'm
accomplishing nothing.
I know I just need to remain
focused on the training.
That's a good mind-set to have.
But the problem is
you're too impatient.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
It was pretty obvious
during our practice.
I'm sorry.
[FO] Don't let your
thoughts get clouded.
Block out everything
that gets in the way.
Or all this work
will be for nothing.
If you keep getting frustrated
over your progress,
then it's just going to
stress you out like before.
You're right.
But, I can promise you
it's not gonna happen again.
Your advice really
helped the other day.
[FO]
Uh?
When you transformed
into Lo Fwa
and told me I should fight for
something worth protecting.
[BAK]
Finally, found you.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[LO FWA]
You mind if we sit with you?
Oh!
You here for lunch, Chief?
Afraid not.
There's something I need
to show all of you.
[BAK] A strange phenomenon
has been observed
while you were training.
I've been monitoring it here.
Using Golems to keep track
of your Innocence level
as you and Fo sparred.
We're looking at
the distribution map.
[BAK]
Now...
Innocence doesn't typically
release high energy
unless it's in a physical form.
But these last two days,
we've seen a spike
in their levels.
Even though yours remains
in a particle state.
Huh?
[BAK] You'll agree it is,
indeed, strange.
So even though my Innocence
isn't in a physical form,
it's still connected to me.
The evidence seems to
point in that direction.
No way!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALLEN]
What's causing it to react?
I want to get your
opinions on the matter.
Why we're encountering
this oddity.
If anyone has a theory,
I'm ready to hear it.
Could be nothing.
No. Say it.
Can't be... But...
Tell us.
[ALLEN]
Hm?
I don't know if it's
related or not.
The past two days, I've
only been thinking about
one thing during
the training sessions.
[BAK]
Whenever you're ready.
Right!
[SHIFU]
The power of thought
is enough to cause
changes to Innocence?
I've never heard of
that occurring.
No one has.
But there's no
other explanation.
The reason you feel
so compelled to fight
is because you have something
important to protect.
[ALLEN]
Something important...
...that I have to protect...
[WONG]
It's happening again!
Just as we predicted,
the readings are spiking!
And they're stronger than
previously recorded!
[BAK] Hm. Then Walker's
hypothesis was correct.
[LO FWA]
Ah! Look!
Do you see that?
The Innocence is glowing!
But why?
Just a guess,
but the energy levels are so
high we can observe it visually.
That's... That's incredible!
Heh. So we are joined.
[LI KEI]
Great job, Walker!
[LO FWA]
We're all cheering for you!
Heh. Thanks!
[ALLEN]
This could be a clue.
Some way to revive my Innocence!
Now's my chance.
I won't let it slip away.
Hey. Walker! Did you already
forget what I said?
Focus on something important!
[ALLEN]
Heh. Right!
[BAK] What did Komui mention
to me over the phone?
If he wants to
activate his power,
then he'll need to
find out what that is.
I think it's something Allen's
longing for at the same time.
I hope that helps.
[BAK]
The "longing" he referred to
could be Allen's feelings
towards his comrades.
His desire to help them
may be the secret
to revitalizing his Innocence.
[groaning]
--What?
--[LI KEI gasps]
Did he hurt himself?
[ALLEN whimpering]
[FO]
What is it?
[gasps]
[ALLEN groans]
[LO FWA]
Allen!
[SHIFU]
Hold on!
[LI KEI]
Are you okay?
What's going on?
What happened?
Do you need a medic?
[ALLEN]
No. I'm fine.
[LO FWA gasps]
[ALLEN grunts]
[LO FWA whimpers]
No. You're not.
[ALLEN gasping]
The experiment is over.
[ALLEN]
Dammit!
You're activating now
when I was so close? Why?
[BAK]
Are you awake?
Chief Bak.
You need to stay in bed!
Don't worry. My eye's
gone back to normal.
The last time it
transformed like that,
you were training
with Fo, right?
Yeah.
[BAK] Afterwards, you told me
it was reacting to Akuma.
Searching for them.
The only thing is I don't
know where they are.
It's like they're
calling out to me.
On top of that, it wasn't
aching like before.
Today was painful.
[BAK]
Calling out?
What do the Akuma want with him?
[ALLEN]
Listen, Bak.
I need you to give
me one more shot.
But this time while
I'm training with Fo!
You're crazy!
If it doesn't activate,
well... not much changes.
All right.
But wait until your
condition improves!
My condition doesn't matter.
Whether I'm feeling
strong or weak,
I have to overcome this!
I'm so close!
We can't waste time worrying
if my eye will ever
stop bothering me.
Walker...
I won't take no for an answer!
You have to let me
resume the training!
You're sure this is
what you want?
Yes. But don't hold back, okay?
Come at me with everything
you've got, Fo.
I want it to activate
no matter what.
Very well. If you insist.
[BOTH grunt]
[yells]
Having second thoughts?
Careful Fo!
She's going too far!
[ALLEN] Concentrate.
What's important to me?
[ALLEN gasping]
[ALLEN]
For the sake of my friends...
...activate!
His Innocence is changing form!
[FO yells]
Innocence!
[FO yelling]
[ALLEN gasping]
[FO grunts]
[panting]
[groans]
Walker.
[ALLEN groans]
No. I want to keep going.
We're not finished yet.
Right.
[ALLEN, FO grunting]
[FO yells]
[ALLEN grunts]
[FO yelps]
[ALLEN]
My... My eye.
The pain is unbearable.
[BAK]
Walker...
[WONG]
Chief Bak! It's Wong!
Report!
[WONG]
Something strange is happening.
I'm detecting abnormally
high energy levels
within his Innocence!
Almost off the charts!
[BAK]
Then he's bearing the pain.
Drowning it out by concentrating
only on his friends.
The focus necessary
must be so intense
it's generating
the surge in power.
[ALLEN]
Almost there...
I can feel it.
[ALLEN]
I'm going back.
[inaudible]
[ALLEN]
Back to my friends.
Are you listening, Innocence?
Then answer!
Activate!
[FO yelling]
[ALLEN]
I don't have time for you!
Stop fighting me!
You're standing in the way
of what's important to me!
[WONG gasps]
[FO groaning]
[ALL groaning]
The Innocence is going
out of control!
Answer me, Innocence.
Why is this happening?
[VOICE]
Don't leave me here.
What?
[VOICE]
I beg you. Help me.
Wait. That voice is a...
[ALLEN screams]
[ALL gasping]
[LO FWA]
Uh?
Why did the wind stop?
[SHIFU]
Allen?
[FO]
Walker!
Go get the medics! Now!
[LI KEI]
Yes sir!
Uh?
[STAFF chattering]
Are those yours?
Allen dropped them
after he passed out.
They must have some
importance to him
so I'm holding onto them
until he wakes up.
Good thinkin'.
Hey, what do you think
happened back there?
I'm not certain, but there's
one thing I'm sure of.
Between his Innocence and eye,
Allen Walker is yielding serious
power. It's incredible.
However, his destiny
is not in his hands.
It's intertwined, guided by
these alarming abilities.
And that's a fate
several times heavier
than us ordinary
humans have to bear.
Bottom line,
he's just like his Innocence.
I think he's beyond
our understanding.
[ALLEN groaning]
[ALLEN]
Innocence.
I have to protect something
important to me.
For the sake of my comrades,
I need you to--
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
That's not the right answer?
My friends aren't
important enough?
Then what do you want to hear?
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN]
What am I doing wrong?
Is there something I'm missing?
Is that why my left eye
is in so much pain?
Tell me... What should I do?
[MANA]
Now, Allen.
You must go deeper into the
realm of black and white.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
I've had that dream before.
Deeper into the realm
of black and white.
[FO]
No problems here.
The outside is clear.
But something's not right...
I sense a presence
probing the barrier
that's protecting our branch.
Who is it?
[AKUMA A]
Oh yes. There it is.
[FO gasps]
[STAFF chattering]
[alarm blares]
[ALL gasp]
[ANNOUNCER A] The barrier
in north passage five
has been compromised.
Security personnel,
report immediately...
If the barrier's compromised,
Fo's in trouble!
[ANNOUNCER A] Security
personnel, report immediately.
[SHIFU, LI KEI, LO FWA panting]
[LO FWA gasps]
[ALLEN]
Is she okay?
That announcement meant
something happened to Fo, right?
Where is she?
Over there.
[ALLEN grunts]
Uh?
[FO groaning]
What the...?
[FO groans]
Bak.
[BAK grunts]
Fo?
Bak...
Bak!
Hide Walker before
it breaks through!
Bak!
No! Fo!
[AKUMA A laughs] So you're the
entrance to the barrier, huh?
There's no way!
How did an Akuma manage to get
through the seal so easily?
It's impossible!
[AKUMA A] Actually, it
required very little effort.
[AKUMA A] My passage here was
granted courtesy of Noah's Ark.
[AKUMA A] Boy with gray
hair, and a strange left eye.
You wouldn't be the
infamous Allen Walker?
[ALLEN]
What?
This feeling.
It's so familiar.
[FO screaming]
[LO FWA]
What's going on?!
That thing... It came
out of Fo's body!
[SHIFU]
My guess is it's an Akuma.
Idiot! Everyone here
knows it's an Akuma!
The issue is, that seal
has been protecting
the Asian Branch for
over a hundred years!
How did it manage to break
through, just like that?
More importantly,
how did it know exactly
where to find Allen?
I've seen those before!
[ALLEN gasping]
[FO]
Walker...
Go... Run!
[ALLEN]
Uh...
This Akuma only has
one goal, to kill you.
The shape you're in,
there's no way you can win!
Get outta here!
I'm not running!
[AKUMA A]
No. I won't allow you to run.
[ALLEN gasps]
[gasping]
[ALLEN groans]
[FO]
Walker!
[ALLEN] An Akuma has
broken through the barrier,
and appeared within the
walls of the Asian Branch.
His ability...
decomposing objects.
If I'm not careful, my left arm
will be the least of my worries.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"Invasion."
[gasping] What the...?