[AGENT A] There goes three
months' worth of salary.
If I stay on as Cross Marian's
caretaker any longer,
I'll end up destitute!
Wait, you did remember to keep
the receipt for that, right?
Even if I proved it was
a business expense,
I doubt Director Rouvelier
would reimburse me.
[AGENT B] Valid point. He holds
the purse strings pretty tight.
[AGENTS gasp]
[AGENT A] What's going on?
Why'd we stop?
[ORDER MEMBER A] It appears the
boat is stuck on something
in the canal.
Perhaps a piece of driftwood?
If we get back late,
we can expect
another scolding
from General Cross.
No thanks!
[gasps]
There's a body under here!
The Oceania Branch Chief.
[ALL scream]
All right. We're ready to work,
what've you got for us to do?
C'mon, guys.
[JOHNNY]
Whoa, hey, you can't come in!
You're not with the
Science Section!
[BAK] So what? I'm still
a damn great scientist!
[RENI] Yeah, you don't
have to be so rude.
You guys are understaffed,
right? Well, we're here to help!
Oh, this is the
last thing I need.
Look, I'm sorry, I'm
not tryin' to be rude.
I'm just tryin' to do
my job, all right?
Sure, and what
important work it is.
[JOHNNY]
Exactly.
Uh.
What?
See. I've got a job to do.
[LULU BELL] You have
the privilege of meeting
the shape-shifting Noah of Lust.
I'm Lulu Bell.
Though we'll be
parting ways soon
as your lives will be ending,
my Master told me to be polite
and introduce myself first.
[gasps]
Allen!
Akuma are here!
I'm picking up a large
number of signals
from the lab I saw Reever in!
The entrance to the lab is
sealed. We've gotta get in!
[LINK] Where did this
black wall come from?
Didn't even make a scratch.
[ALLEN]
Look out, Lavi!
Let's try Heaven Compass!
With Edge End!
Did it work?
[LAVI] Nothing.
So how do we get through?
I can't hear anything
from the other side.
Are they here for the egg?
To steal back the factory?
All I know is Reever
and the rest of the Science
Section are trapped!
We've gotta find a way
to break down this wall!
[LINK]
You're wasting your time!
Follow me!
You're not to come with
us, Lavi. Understand?
Come on! I like a joke,
but now's not the time!
[BOOKMAN]
I'm serious.
Your Innocence hasn't
been repaired yet.
Your presence would only
slow down the rest of us.
Tell everyone what's happening!
Go spread the word!
[rumbling]
[BOOKMAN]
Hm?
The Master's egg is ours
again. Safe and sound.
Kill me. Just kill me already.
[RENI] What the hell
are the Akuma up to?
They're lining the
researchers up in rows.
Whatever it is,
I guarantee it's not good.
Chief Bak. Is that you?
[BAK]
Johnny. You're finally awake.
Chief. Take off my headphones.
Listen to them. Please.
[REEVER]
Hello? Can you hear me?
It's Reever! So you're
still alive, huh?
You sound surprised, Chief
Bak. Good to hear you.
It could be the number of Akuma,
but the radio signal is so weak,
we can't communicate
outside the lab.
[BAK] Are you the only
one who wasn't captured?
Negative. There's
five others here.
Listen, I don't know
if you started,
but you should rig up
a barrier talisman.
Way ahead of you. Though I
don't know if it'll function.
We're doing what we can, but
there's not a lot to work with.
[REEVER]
Same story over here.
[RENI] Bak! Something else is
coming through using their Ark.
We've already lined
them up for you.
Make it quick. We don't
have much time.
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am.
[SKULL A]
Who do we have first?
Let's see if this one has a
good head on their shoulders.
Hmm...
[SKULL A]
X.
The ones marked X we don't need.
[SKULL A]
Who's next?
[SCIENTIST A screams]
They're killing them! Dammit!
[BAK]
Reever! Don't!
Even if we attacked all at once,
we wouldn't stand a chance
against their numbers.
The best thing we can do is to
survive as long as possible.
Keep working on the talisman
and we may be able
to save a few.
Don't give up, Reever!
We may not be able to
reach the outside,
but we still have
Walker's left eye.
He definitely noticed
what's going on.
Don't lose faith!
Tup's out there!
[SCIENTIST A]
There he is, Section Leader!
[REEVER]
Tup!
You damn skeleton!
What do you think
you're gonna do to me?
Well now, this one talks.
We're creating puppets
to guard the egg.
Skulls, as the Noah call us.
It's a necessity to
recruit more of our kind
since your Exorcists
killed so many of us.
First, I need to judge
if you're worthy.
Just you wait!
You'll pay for this!
[SKULL A]
I've got good news.
Your brain makes you the perfect
candidate to join our ranks.
Congratulations.
On.
[TUP screaming]
They're gonna kill him!
Do something!
[TUP screaming]
[SKULL A]
Abata. Ura. Masarakato.
On Magjijba. Kiiki.
[SCIENTIST D]
Tup?
The first conversion of the day.
You'll get a uniform later.
Tup? No way.
It can't be. It's not real!
Will you be as lucky?
[SCIENTIST D]
Somebody... Help me.
[grunts]
My head.
[REEVER]
I won't let you hurt another!
I'm Reever Wenhamm.
Science Section Leader.
And I've got the largest brain
here, so just try and take it.
[BOTH]
Section Leader!
What's he doing?
Stopping them!
You imbeciles! Get down
before they spot us!
[REEVER] Tup. What
have they done to you?
He's still my subordinate,
and if you really want him,
you'll have to go through me!
I accept.
A Section Leader, huh?
You'll make a fine
addition to our cause.
You. Allen!
[ALL gasp]
If it isn't Allen Walker.
I'll make you pay for this.
You won't get away!
[ALLEN]
I'll make you pay for this.
You won't get away!
[ALLEN]
Lulu Bell.
What've you done?
Retaliation for the
damage you've caused.
The egg is coming with me.
Hear me, Akuma!
Don't let the Exorcist
anywhere near our prize.
[AKUMA laughing]
Crown Clown activate!
Did you see that? The kid's
gotten even stronger.
Kill them. Please.
Avenge our colleagues.
Heaven Compass!
[yelling]
The Innocence,
it has begun to develop
unprecedented properties.
[gasps] It's evolving?
Are you saying the Innocence
has begun to evolve?
[KOMUI]
Is that possible?
Perhaps it is.
But the stronger it grows,
the more it demands of its host.
Like a Parasite Type.
[LENALEE] Which means my life
will be shortened by its power.
[HEVLASKA]
I suggest that she is prepared.
[LENALEE]
I'm ready.
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A]
Enemy attack!
Attention all Exorcists and
Black Order Personnel!
Akuma in Lab 5!
[LENALEE]
Lab 5?
That's where everyone from
the Science Section is!
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A]
Currently, two Exorcists
are battling with the intruders.
The following Generals
and Exorcists
report to Gate 3 of
the Ark immediately.
Noise Marie.
Miranda Lotto.
Report to Gate 3 at once.
But, Maosa!
You know your weapon
isn't ready yet, Chaozii.
I'm afraid you'll just
have to sit this one out.
Let's go, Maosa.
[LENALEE] Only two Exorcists.
And I bet one of them is Allen!
That's strange.
My legs feel so light.
I wonder if I'm not
feeling any pain
because I'm not wearing
the dark boots anymore.
All this time, I didn't realize
how heavy those shoes were.
How much they punished my feet.
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A]
Where are you going, Lavi?
I reported the attack!
Now I gotta be off!
What the--?
[LENALEE]
Come on, Lavi!
[LAVI]
Lenalee?
Where do you think
you're goin' barefoot?
[LENALEE] Do you know what floor
the elevator is on right now?
I need to see Hevlaska!
[LENALEE]
Komui!
We need to speak, Lavi.
[LENALEE]
Komui! Wait!
[LAVI] What're you doin'?
Let us outta here!
[HEAD NURSE A]
Settle down.
[LENALEE]
Head nurse?
Why is the doctor in here?
[HEAD NURSE A]
This is Count Krory's sickroom.
We're in charge
of caring for him
since he hasn't woken up yet.
[KOMUI] The room is
protected by a barrier
and designated as an evacuation
area for noncombatants.
The two of you will remain here.
We're looking for Kanda
and Chaozii as well.
I gotta help the old man!
You're crazy if you think
I'm stayin' in here!
[KOMUI] With what weapons?
Your hammer's broken.
And that's the reason I told
you to hurry up and repair it!
You need to hire more
techs, you idiot!
You have to let me talk
to Hevlaska, Komui!
I can still fight!
All I need is to synchronize
with my Innocence!
How, may I ask, do you
intend to do that?
The last time you
tried to equip,
your synchronization rate
was less than ten percent.
Besides--
[LENALEE] I saw an experiment!
A long time ago!
Experiment?
They-They were trying
to make Exorcists.
Isn't that right?
I'll beg Hevlaska.
Ask her to implant an
Innocence in my body.
I know for a fact the people
in those experiments
weren't Accomodators.
But since I am, I may be able
to respond to the Innocence
where they couldn't.
Are you out of your mind?
Let's pretend for a moment
Hevlaska did agree.
If you fail, then the Innocence
could go out of control!
[LENALEE] Hevlaska was
the one who told me
I needed to be ready!
I bet the Innocence is
testing me! I'm sure of it!
All I have to do is show
I'm willing to risk my life.
I think I'll be able to
fully synchronize with it!
Then, once I prove
myself... it'll work.
And I'll be able to
save them. Everyone.
I'd be able to save
you, big brother.
[KOMUI]
You're willing to die?
You don't care what
happens to your life
as long as it means, in the end,
you'll save mine
or someone else's?
[KOMUI]
What am I saying?
No, it's not... like that.
[KOMUI]
I'm the one...
[LENALEE]
Big brother. Can you hear me?
[KOMUI] ...the one who
drove her to this point.
[KOMUI]
Please, Lenalee. Stay in there.
[KOMUI] Despite my best efforts,
I know I can't keep avoiding it,
but... maybe I can delay it.
Brother... Please.
[KOMUI]
I almost lost you once.
I'm not ready to send
you to Hevlaska.
[COMMUNICATION MEMBER A] Chief!
Marie and Miranda have arrived!
[KOMUI]
I'll be right there.
[KOMUI] Hurry up and locate
Kanda and Chaozii!
[GUARD A]
Yes, sir!
[beeping]
[LINK]
Director.
I read you loud and clear.
Out of curiosity,
were you the one
that permitted Allen
Walker to use the Ark?
[LINK]
Yes, sir. Accept my apologies.
Save your breath, Inspector.
I was intending to
use Walker as a pawn.
The most important thing
is keeping the egg
under our control.
We've come too far
to let it slip back
into the hands of our enemy.
They'll be okay.
Heaven Compass! Get on, boy!
[yells]
How disruptive.
[LULU BELL]
Skull. Don't get distracted.
Proceed with the conversion
while you still have time.
Yes.
We'll withdraw once the
egg is placed in the Ark.
Akuma, until that happens,
hold the Exorcists back.
[AKUMAS roaring]
[ALLEN]
There's too many of them!
Now, gate, open.
[ALL gasp]
We lost the egg to you once.
I'll make sure that
never happens again.
[ALLEN] The Order has been
overrun by a horde of Akuma.
Though Bookman and I fight
with everything we've got,
Lulu Bell's troops overwhelm us.
Maybe the arrival
of four Generals
will help even the odds.
On the next D.Gray-man:
"The Power of Generals."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul
[MIRANDA screams]
Watch out!
Uh?
[KANDA]
Huh?
Lulu Bell!
You know that swimsuit
isn't school sanctioned!
The coach didn't seem
to have a problem.
I think we can make
an exception.
[LENALEE]
Huh?
[LAVI, BOOKMAN]
A big exception!