[ALLEN]
Ready when you are.
So how many times do you
wanna be killed today?
I'm slightly impressed that
you haven't run away yet.
[ALLEN] We're not stopping
until I'm satisfied.
[FO] And when do you
expect that to happen?
When my arm returns.
When my Innocence comes back.
That's fine.
[FO yells]
[ALLEN grunts]
[FO]
Got you!
[BOTH grunting]
[ALLEN groans]
[FO yells]
Activate now!
[WONG] Allen Walker's
fighting style has improved
considerably since yesterday.
It's truly amazing.
But pointless.
I admit his arm has adapted,
however, only to its
current unstable form.
It doesn't matter how
much of his strength
returns or his skill improves.
Our goal is to revive
his Innocence.
Unless that happens, he'll
never be an Exorcist again.
[WONG]
Huh?
[BAK] And at this rate, we still
have a long road ahead of us.
[CREW snoring]
[BOOKMAN]
Hm...
Hm?
Uh! [chuckles]
[gasping]
[ALLEN gasping]
Give me your hand!
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN]
Take the girl!
[LENALEE]
I can't save her if I stay here!
I have to find her treatment.
Hold on, Allen! I won't be long.
I guess this must be
where they parted ways.
Allen met with a Noah, and
it destroyed his left arm.
The only thing he could do
was save Suman's Innocence.
[LENALEE]
It's blood.
He was right here.
But now he's gone.
How are we going to find him?
[WONG] I hope you've
said your goodbyes,
because you need to
leave immediately.
Our goodbyes?
What are you saying?
Is he dead already?
I know that it's
difficult to hear,
but you need to do as I ask.
[LENALEE whimpers]
Lenalee, you saw Tim's memory
just the same as I did.
Allen lost his left arm
back there, remember?
That alone means he can't
be an Exorcist anymore.
We have to accept
that and move on.
[glass shatters]
[LAVI]
I've told you a million times!
There was nothing we could do!
I mean, come on,
this is war, Lenalee!
We have to move forward!
[LENALEE sighs]
[gasps]
[ANITA]
We're about halfway there.
The weather isn't bad.
If it holds, we should be able
to reach Edo in two days.
Provided we don't
run into trouble.
[knocking]
[ANITA]
Yes? Who is it?
Forgive me for bothering
you, Anita. It's late.
But I was wondering,
could I borrow something
to tie my hair back?
These used to belong to my
mother. Do you like them?
What? You must treasure them.
Are you sure it's okay?
Of course.
Her original intention was
to pass them down to me
on my 18th birthday.
But she was killed by an Akuma
before that day could arrive.
I could never bring
myself to wear them.
Killed by an Akuma.
I'm sorry to be asking this,
but your mother supported the
Black Order as well, didn't she?
Yes. She fell in love
with General Cross
the moment she saw him and that
was that. Classic love story.
Oh. I imagine it was.
[ANITA]
It's hard for me to understand.
He really is such
a troublesome man.
I wish I had gotten the
chance to ask her why
she kept loving him for so long.
But then again who am I
to judge? I'm the same.
[sighs]
[CROSS] Be honest.
You hate me, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I see.
Anita!
[ANITA]
Mm? Yes?
One day, you'll be just
like your mother. I'm sure.
[gasps] I don't care.
After all, everything I'm doing
is because of that man.
So I can be of help to him.
Everything to help him.
Do you think General
Cross is out there?
That's he's still alive?
I believe so. I have to.
It's the only thing
that gives me strength.
I understand.
[BOOKMAN]
Don't get caught up in the war.
You are the successor to a
Bookman, no more, and no less.
You are not an Apostle of God.
Have I not always taught
you that your role
is as a bystander,
not a participant?
I'm not their ally.
[BOOKMAN]
The only reason we happen to be
on the Order's side
is to record.
Do not forget your
purpose, Lavi.
[LAVI]
We're just here to keep records.
That's all. Nothing more.
Bookmen don't get attached.
They don't need feelings.
[KRORY]
Checkmate, old man.
Now wait just a minute!
Oh, no.
What's going on, Miranda?
Is there some sort of problem?
[MIRANDA] It isn't good.
Right now part of the ship
is experiencing repeated
time recoveries.
It's coming from...
...above us.
The ship's deck
is being attacked!
[BOTH gasping]
[CREW panting]
[ANITA]
What's wrong?
[MAHOJA]
Watchman! Report! What happened?
[MAHOJA grunts]
[ANITA]
Hurry!
[LENALEE]
Right!
The second mast is shattered!
[coughs]
[MAHOJA]
By what?
[BOOKMAN, KRORY, LENALEE gasp]
[CREW E yelps]
An Akuma?
Only one?
Where's Lavi?
[ESHI] I think I'll title this
one "Corpse of an Exorcist."
[LAVI] Devouring Flame!
Direct Fire Stamp!
Dammit! I could've done
without those injuries!
New title:
[LAVI]
Huh?
[ESHI] "Why Does This Exorcist
Keep Recovering?"
[LAVI] I can't believe it.
That didn't affect him at all.
[ALL gasping]
How can that be?
[LAVI grunts]
Damn.
Come on. It should
be crushing him!
There's no way.
You must be a Level Three.
[LAVI yelps]
[CREW gasping]
Lavi!
Your title: "The Crushed Skull"!
[LAVI]
It's over.
[MAHOJA]
Lavi!
[ANITA]
Uh...
[KRORY grunts]
[MIRANDA gasps]
[LENALEE gasps]
Lavi!
[LAVI gasps]
Your title: "The Crushed Skull"!
[LAVI]
It's over.
[MIRANDA gasping]
This isn't my art.
[BOOKMAN] Heaven Compass
Binding Spell Needles.
North Crime!
[ESHI]
Ah!
[ESHI groaning]
No way!
You had me scared there
for a second, you idiot!
[LAVI gasping]
I got ya!
[LAVI grunts]
Nice catch.
[ESHI] Title: "Why Don't You
Finish Me Off Already?"
Oh, I intend to,
but first there are a few
questions I need you to answer.
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
[ESHI] "Eshi was Created from
the Soul of a Japanese Artist."
That's my title.
[BOOKMAN] You didn't travel
all the way out to the middle
of the ocean just to hunt
humans for fun, did you?
Are you under orders
from the Earl?
[ESHI] Heh. I'd've expected
you wanted information
on Cross Marian.
[BOOKMAN]
Hm?
[ESHI groans, screams]
[BOOKMAN]
Impossible!
[ESHI]
Title: "A Reversal of Fortune."
[ESHI] I can tell you about
him on one condition.
You agree to be a
model for my art.
[BOOKMAN]
You're a Level Three Akuma!
Let him go! Extend!
Lavi!
[MIRANDA]
I should have told him.
He can't move too far
away from the ship.
Bookman! Lavi!
[MAHOJA]
What now?
[ANITA]
Don't lose that Akuma!
All hands! Report to
your battle stations!
[CREW]
Right!
[gasps]
I title this...
"Old Man and the Moon."
[LAVI]
No.
Old man! Come on! Please!
Wake up!
[LAVI]
Old man!
[ESHI chuckles]
[LAVI]
Uh... Uh!
[MIRANDA cries]
[LAVI]
That was close.
[LENALEE]
Innocence! Level Two Release!
Lenalee...
Dammit! What's going
on with Lavi?
Is Bookman okay?
Who is that?
Lenalee?
[LENALEE] You need to
head back to the ship!
[LAVI]
Lenalee! Hold on! Don't go!
His power is way different from
the Akuma we've fought before!
He's a Level Three!
You can't fight him alone!
[LAVI gasping]
[LAVI] My injuries. Why are
they coming back now?
I must be too far
away from the ship.
Dammit...
Uh. Lenaleee!
[ESHI chuckles]
[ESHI]
I'll title you...
[LENALEE yells]
[ESHI]
You're fast.
[LENALEE yells]
[gasps]
The perfect title:
"Are you next?"
Self titled. Cause I'm
going to destroy you!
[ALLEN] As the ship is being
destroyed from a skyward attack,
Miranda and the rest of the crew
struggle to keep it afloat.
Meanwhile, Lenalee
fights against Eshi,
a Level Three Akuma.
Will she survive without
the help of her allies?
On the next D. Gray-Man :
"Sinking Darkness."
Kanda. Do you feel like
playin' a card game?
Say what?
Then again,
we don't have to since
I know I'm going to win.
Cut the deck!
[ALLEN] A royal flush.
Can you beat that?
It looks like a bunch
of random cards.
It looks like a win to me.
[KANDA growls] I don't play
your Western card games!
This pair is one of a kind.
Hey, Allen. Do you want
to play a card game?
[ALLEN]
Huh?
We're playing Old Maid, huh?
Is this game more
your speed, Kanda?
[LAVI]
Heh.
Kanda goes well with the Joker!
The perfect match!
My sword goes well with
your face, short stack!
They're all really good
friends, as you can see.