When it's finished, everyone
will know I'm a genius!
Please?
Alright then...
I'm so glad!
No problem.
Hey there, Lenalee!
Komui?
Well, don't you two seem
to be having such fun...!
What are you talking about?
You know how much
I love a good conversation!
I'll just catch up
with you in a bit.
Thanks, Russell...
We'll chat soon.
Lenalee... what was
all that about dear?
I already forgot...!
I'll see you later, okay?
Suspicious...
What could my sweet
Lenalee, be hiding?
Reever!
Yeah?
It looks like you
guys are busy as usual.
Oh, Allen...
Yeah, the Chief keeps sending
us one task after another.
What?!
You're going out?!
Uh-huh...!
I haven't had a day
off in a long time!
Lenalee...
Ah...! She is... pretty...
Oh, no! I was just...
Lenalee...!
Where you off to?
Just to town to
do some shopping...
...that is... if my brother
here will let go of me.
That's not a good plan...!
That town is
extremely dangerous!
Yeah, but Lenalee's tough,
so you don't have
to worry, right?
I am pretty tough...
Alright... see ya later!
Have a good time, Lenalee!
No...! Wait! Lenalee!
Excuse me, Chief...
...but I think it's
time we got to work.
Ahh!
Let go of me, Section Leader!
Let me go!
Take your hands off me Reever...
Hey, uh... where's Mr. Russell?
Oh... Oh, Russell,
it's his day off...
Come to think of it,
I'm pretty sure he was
headed into town, too.
Did he say Russell was in town?
Could he and Lenalee...
No! I have to stop them!
Ya think the Chief's... alright?
Don't know.
Chief?
I brought the results
of the analysis!
Komui?
I wonder where he ran off to...
There's trouble!
Section Leader Reever, hurry!
The storage room in the basement
has been unsealed and
Sir Komlin the Second is gone!
What?!
You're kidding!
Russell, you lecherous fiend!
It can't be coincidence they
were so secretive earlier,
and they both just happened
to go into town today?!
Oh yes, it's perfectly clear
that they're dating...!
How disgusting!!
And they've taken to
sneaking out together...!
Dear Lenalee,
I did not raise you
to be dishonest and
immoral, young lady!
Hear me now, Sir Komlin...!
Use your upgrade to
stop this relationship!
Exorcists... where are they?!
What are you yelling about?!
Quiet!
This is shameful--I
am an Akuma...!
When I was a Level One
I was able to take
human life quite easily...
but at Level Two
I haven't killed
even a single one--what
am I doing wrong?!
I must pull myself together...!
After all, I do have a perfect
transformation ability.
Now, transform!
So handsome!
So it seems I can convince
even the animals
with my disguises...
My transformation
ability is quite phenomenal!
Is it possible
that the perfection
of this valuable skill has
caused me to lose all of my--
Oh, no... it can't be true.
I managed to get this
picture of an Exorcist...!
I'll kill her and bid farewell
to my old, pathetic self.
Wow... she's pretty!
How lucky...!
I'm not so pathetic, after all!
What's happening?!
Targets locked on, Lenalee...
Russell...
I don't understand!
Mama, what's that?
Shh, come on; don't
look it in the eye!
That's funny...
Filthy octopus...!
Trying to put his hands
all over my sweet Lenalee...!
Upgraded Sir Komlin,
eliminate Russell the pervert!
Oh my...
Let go of me...!
I have to kill him!
I have to kill that pervert...
Please, Chief, you're
going to have to calm down!
Using Sir Komlin like this
could easily destroy the
town if you're not careful!
The most important matter
is my Lenalee's safety,
so what if we have to
sacrifice a town or two...
Okay, this obsession
is getting kind of sick.
Allen... deal with this please.
Yes, sir!
Ahhh...!
My upgraded Sir Komlin!
Allen, you idiot
octopus helper outer...
Hey, what is this thing...?!
It won't come off!
That's a good look for you!
I've got just the
thing for that pervert...
Ahh...! Step away
from the gun...!
Please, Chief Komui!
Do you believe he
was really intending
to use all these
octopi on Russell?!
Come on now,
Chief, think about it!
Your sister and Russell are
just walking around together
and talking, that doesn't
mean they're dating, does it?!
Do they look like they just
happened to run into each other?
You know Russell has a son,
don't you, Chief...?!
That means he's
probably way too old
to make a move on
Lenalee, wouldn't ya say?
Let's just wait and see, okay?
I'll, reserve judgment.
However...
If I discover they're dating
the jerk will have
nowhere to hide!
It looks like a shop
for men's clothes.
I knew it! They're dating!
You can't know that based on
what kind of store
they walked into, Chief!
Ahh, it's no use...!
I can't get it off!
May I help you?
Do you have a good tie
selection?
Certainly, Miss... this way.
What do you think of this one?
Let me see...
They haven't noticed
that I'm an Akuma...
I'm able to fool
even the Exorcists...
My transformation ability is
absolutely very, very perfect!
Pardon me.
No... I won't...
I won't allow it!
I'll take care of
that fiend Russell
by blowing him and everything
else on Earth to smithereens!
We need some help, Allen!
Allen is busy fighting
the octopus, sir.
Timcanpy, pull harder!
Fine, then you do it, Lavi!
Okay...
We're saved...
Hey!
One way or another, he will die!
Sorry, Chief...
Here's my chance...
Oh no, was the
wall weak or something?
I don't understand!
What the hell do you
think you're doing...?!
You blew half of the
store away, Chief!
Do not be alarmed,
that bomb was programmed
to hurt everyone except
my dear sweet Lenalee.
You are missing the point, sir!
I can't get it off of me!
I'm begging you...
Leave this café alone...
Are you listening
to me, Chief...?
Don't do anything to
jeopardize these people.
I'm rather uncomfortable
taking orders
from a man wearing a dress.
Oh really, and just
why do you suppose
we're dressed up this way?!
Don't look at me...
Okay go ahead.
Pull it, don't worry about me!
Sorry to keep you waiting...
Why... thank you!
You're welcome, Miss, enjoy.
Now drink up...
drink your poisoned tea...
One sip will send you
to the Netherworld.
How many sugars
do you usually take?
Oh... I'll do that myself.
Fly my pink fuzzy ones...
Destroy Russell!!
Lavi!
Yes, sir... Grow!
Wow... again?
Why... Why me?
Damn you--
Did you see their hands?!
Anyone would have
thought they were dating...
This time she'll die for sure!
Mr. Russell, come in here!
What?
I was looking at this one!
Ah, yes, that's a
very good choice!
The charade ends
now, Russell...!
Number sixty-five!
Yes, sir!
Move out...
Macho number sixty-five!
Attack!
Just give it a rest!
Was that a dart...?!
Damn you, Chief,
I'm gettin' super sleepy...
Give that to me. Take it, men!
Man, this has been
happening all day!
Enough is enough,
you have to stop this!
But he but they
but but but I can't--
No... No more!
Chief, please, you
have to calm down!
I can't bear any
more mistakes...!
I have to take my chance now.
I wonder what
happened to the lights?
Don't worry...
It's probably just a blackout.
I'm sure the lights
will come back on soon.
Exorcist, prepare to die!
My Lenalee!
Komui what... What are
you doing in town?
Russell, you won't
get away with this!
Stand by...! Sir Komlin
the Third deploy!
I'm the only one
who falls on her...
Well, I... I don't...
I don't know what's going on,
but there's no reason for
you to be so upset, brother.
Be quiet, quiet, quiet!
Oh, no...
Is that...
Komlin?
Sir Komlin the Third!
And now, Sir Komlin...!
We will annihilate Russell!
Komlin... Punch!
There's no escape!
Hey, stop, quit it!
Unreal...
Faster!
Jump!
Komlin Kick!
I... I'm not that Russell
person I swear to you...
I'm really an Akuma!
You're exactly right,
anyone seducing Lenalee
get's treated like an Akuma...!
Komlin High Beam!
Come on... Lavi...
You've got to help
us stop the Chief!
I... I can't...
Allen!
Komlin High Beam!
Say hi to Sir Komlin the Third's
killer technique, Russell...
Komlin Fist--
What are you doing
here, brother...?
Answer me!
I don't care what you do,
I won't accept it, Lenalee...
Russell can't be your boyfriend!
My boyfriend...?!
You think Mr. Russell is...
Where in the world did
you come up with that?!
But the two of you
went on a secret date!
I saw it all with
my own eyes, the horror!
Geez...
Russell! Are you
alright, buddy?!
Here.
What's this?
It's a present for you...
I came to town today to buy it.
A present for... me?
I asked Mr. Russell
to come with me
to help pick
something out for you,
and then I thought
I would return the favor
by helping him find a really
nice present for his son, John.
Well gosh, I certainly wish
you'd told me all
of this sooner...!
Sir Komlin...! You
may stop the attack!
That was too close!
I think it's safe to
say we're done here!
Mr. Russell, I'm sorry for the
trouble my brother has caused.
Oh... no problem.
Thank you and I believe
we did have a deal
so let's go and find that
present for John.
At last, I can finally kill her!
Lenalee!
Why am I such a bad Akuma...!
I guess I'm glad the
pretty girl gets to live!
Don't worry, everyone, I'm here!
Thank you, Allen, you--
Where's Mr. Russell?
The real Mr. Russell
is just fine.
I'm so glad,
but why do you think that
Akuma was just targeting me?
I really have no idea.
Woo-hoo...!
I got a present from Lenalee...!
She got it just for me...!
A present, a
present, woo-hoo...!
Uh-oh...
I think you've done
enough damage today!
Sir Komlin...
Sleep...
My sweet...
So what are we going
to do about this mess?
I propose we all pitch
in to fix the damage...
I'll leave you to it while
I go visit Sir Komlin...
Let's get to work!
He plays with a robot
while we're cleaning up,
all those in favor of burying
him in one of these walls?
Let's get him.
What's the matter, everyone...?
Ow, that looks sharp...
In searching for
traces of my Master,
I travel to a small village,
where I am asked to
face off against a vampire.
On the next episode
of D.Gray-man:
"Vampire of the
Solitary Castle."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul!