[groaning]
Mugen. Bring forth calamity!
Now, Nigen Swords!
[LAVI]
Be careful, Yu!
That thing's ridiculously
hard to...
[HUGE AKUMA B screams]
...kill...
Lavi. Listen.
[LAVI]
Y-Yeah?
If I ever hear you refer to
me by my first name again,
you're a dead man.
[LAVI]
You're as scary as ever.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Such impudence!
That must be...
[gasps]
What is that?
Look out!
[KRORY, BOOKMAN grunt]
Miranda!
Please, speak to me!
Come on... Wake up!
[MIRANDA groaning]
[CHAOZII]
No, it's too late!
[KANDA grunts]
[KANDA grunting]
[LENALEE gasps]
Lavi!
[LAVI]
Uh!
Well, that was scary!
Lenalee, are you okay out there?
[LENALEE]
I'm sorry.
You're always saving me.
That's not the Lenalee I know.
Let's win this
and go home, okay?
[LENALEE]
Huh?
Mm!
[LAVI]
Here. This way.
[BOTH grunting]
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI]
Lenalee!
Time to disappear.
My!
You are nothing if not
thorough, Lord Millennium.
I'm rather impressed!
Edo is completely annihilated.
[MILLENNIUM EARL sneezes]
[SKINN]
Huh...?
Uh...
[MILLENNIUM EARL sneezing]
[LERO] Are you all right,
Lord Millennium, Lero?
Oops, your nose
is running, Lero!
[MILLENNIUM EARL coughs]
[TYKI] Oh. I've got eyes
on an Exorcist here.
And he's still in one piece.
[KANDA grunting]
Damn you...
You won't defeat me. Bastards!
[TIEDOLL]
Marie.
Can you hear me?
[MARIE]
Y... Yes, Master.
[TIEDOLL]
Are you injured?
[MARIE]
I'll... I'll be all right.
What on earth was that?
[TIEDOLL] It must have been
the Earl's special ability.
It's nothing short of a genuine
miracle that you all survived.
[MARIE grunts]
[TIEDOLL] Can you check
on the others for me?
Yes, sir.
No. The Cross Unit's heartbeats
are even fainter than ours are.
And some of them are
barely managing to hold on.
[LENALEE]
Every...one...
Please...
That was insane. What happened?
[gasps]
[MIRANDA whimpering]
Wait, Exorcist Miranda!
No way! Did you use
your power to protect us?
I can fix what's broken,
but my clock can't do
anything for the dead.
[CHAOZII gasps]
And I...
I wasn't quick enough
to bring everyone back.
[LENALEE]
Miranda...
[LAVI groans]
Hold on, Lenalee.
[LAVI groaning]
[LAVI]
Damn!
[LAVI grunting]
[LENALEE]
Lavi.
[LAVI]
Uh?
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI gasping]
Again?
[KANDA]
Hey. What is that?
What's going on?
[LENALEE]
Kanda.
[gasps]
[LENALEE]
Lavi.
[LAVI gasps]
[KANDA grunts]
[LENALEE]
Everyone...
Is that... really?
It's Lenalee.
[LENALEE]
You guys. I'm here!
[MARIE] Hm? Is that
really Lenalee's voice?
I've never heard anything
like it before.
Oh, Lenalee.
[TIEDOLL]
Hm? That voice is...
What was that?
So you heard it, too?
[SKINN]
Yeah.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
How truly bizarre.
[TYKI]
Yeah?
What's that?
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Who'd have thought
such a thing would ever
possibly happen?
Heh. This is most unusual.
[KANDA]
You're saying the Innocence
decided to protect Lenalee's
life of its own free will?
[LAVI]
Yeah.
But she has an
Equipment Type Innocence.
It can't!
Most of them can't.
But this one...
Well, it seems to
be a special kind.
A special kind?
[gasps]
Don't tell me!
Is this...?
[LENALEE]
Everyone!
[BOOKMAN]
Come to think of it,
Miss Lena's Innocence has
voluntarily changed its form
once before in order to
save its owner from dying.
The fact that such a phenomenon
is occurring a second time
could be a sign that...
[TIEDOLL] If this is true, then
the Innocence Lenalee possesses
is of a rare variety that's
extremely valuable to our team.
And to the Millennium Earl.
[MARIE]
What a sound.
[TIEDOLL]
Careful, Marie!
The Earl has his eye on Lenalee!
[MARIE gasps]
Look above you!
Kanda! Lavi!
[gasps]
Whoa!
That really the best you can do?
You're not half bad.
Sorry, but the girl is mine!
[gasps]
[KANDA growls]
[LAVI]
Yu!
[yells]
[KANDA grunts]
Uh-oh.
Now you can't swing that
flashy sword anymore.
[TYKI]
My apologies.
As much as I'd like to keep
having fun with you,
the circumstances
won't allow it.
It's the end of the
world as you know it.
[KANDA gasps]
[TYKI]
I can't wait to watch!
[KANDA] You don't seem
to actually understand
what's happening. You might
be the one who disappears.
Huh?
That expression. It's perfect.
[TYKI]
This is your final moment.
Take a good hard look!
[TYKI gasps]
Mugen.
Nigen Swords!
[TYKI]
Huh?
Almost had me.
[TYKI chuckles]
Oh my, now it's
getting interesting!
Shut up!
You haven't changed
at all, have you?
[LAVI gasping]
Do you like sweets? 'Cause I do!
[LENALEE]
Lavi!
[SKINN]
Huh? Hm?
[LAVI yelling]
[SKINN groans]
I'll crush you!
Grow...
Grow.
Grow!
[SKINN groans]
[SKINN]
Never, ever forgive!
[LAVI gasps]
[LAVI screams]
[LAVI groaning]
[LENALEE]
Lavi!
No!
[LAVI groans]
[SKINN] Coming at me like that
after taking such a hard hit?
You have got some
real nerve, buddy.
[gasping]
And right when we
might've finally found
just what we've
been looking for.
Thanks for ruining the mood!
[LAVI gasping]
[LAVI] So, they really
are after Lenalee.
[LAVI]
No.
I mean.
Am I still a part of this world?
[LAVI gasping]
I can't give up.
[SKINN]
Listen to me.
I'll never forgive any of you.
I won't forgive you damn
Exorcists, not ever!
[LAVI groaning]
[MARIE]
Lavi... Wake up!
Lavi!
[LAVI grunting]
[SKINN groaning]
Marie!
[MARIE] I can only keep him
restrained for so long!
Lavi, can you get on your feet?
[LAVI grunts]
[LAVI]
Yeah. I think I can handle it.
Oh, you still want to fight
after the beating you just took?
I don't care how many of you
damn Exorcists I'm up against,
I'll still win.
Don't be so sure.
[LENALEE]
You guys!
[MIRANDA gasps]
Lenalee!
Hey, what's wrong, Miranda?
Did you just hear something?
Oh, no.
It's nothing to worry about,
but still, thank you for asking.
That's good to hear.
You know, I never realized
that Innocence was capable
of this kind of thing.
I know it's temporary,
but it's amazing that
you can heal their wounds.
[MIRANDA] Well, if the
circumstances were different,
I would prefer not
to use this ability.
[CHAOZII]
Huh?
[MIRANDA]
Even if they regain
the strength to
fight temporarily,
they're just going to keep
sustaining injuries.
The longer it takes to bring
this battle to an end,
the more likely
we'll lose someone.
And then I won't be
able to revive them!
I wish I were able to
help fight, but I...
I can't!
--[crash]
--[gasps]
[HUGE AKUMA A roars]
[CHAOZII] Looks like
the Akuma's on the move!
Lenalee!
[gasps] You must be...
[TIEDOLL]
Mm.
Don't move.
O, Maker of Eden!
Activate!
And acknowledge the beauty
that's in the world!
Art!
[HUGE AKUMA A roars]
[LAVI]
What just happened?
[MARIE]
That's our Master's Innocence.
I've never seen it in
that capacity though!
[SKINN]
Heads up, punk!
[MARIE groans]
Marie!
[SKINN laughs]
Oh, I can't wait to
destroy all of you!
It's gonna be so sweet!
[TYKI]
You shouldn't be so stubborn.
People hate that.
[KANDA]
Shut up!
[HUGE AKUMA A roars]
[LENALEE]
Let me out!
Lenalee!
Oh, no.
[LENALEE]
Please listen to me!
I'm an Exorcist too.
I can help you defeat them!
Just let me out! Hurry!
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Sure, why not?
[LENALEE gasps]
[MILLENNIUM EARL grunts]
[TIEDOLL grunts]
[gasps]
[LAVI gasps]
You're wastin' your time.
No matter how hard you try, your
power can never break into it.
[KANDA grunting]
Now you've gone
and made me angry.
[LENALEE]
Uh!
[EVIL SPIRITS laughing]
[LENALEE whimpering]
[LENALEE gasping]
[MILLENNIUM EARL laughing]
[LENALEE screams]
[LENALEE]
Uh?
[LENALEE gasps]
What the...?
Look at the sky. It split open.
[MILLENNIUM EARL]
Why good evening.
What a surprise
to see you again...
...Allen Walker!
[LENALEE gasping]
[ALLEN]
Hmph.
Hello, Earl. Good evening.
[ALLEN]
My recently revived Innocence
enters a fierce one-on-one duel
against the Millennium Earl
and his devastating weapon.
At that moment, the battle
reaches a brand new stage.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"Clown and Auguste."
Bring forth salvation to
this poor Akuma's soul!
You won't beat me. Never!
Hey Kanda, your hair
keeps fallin' in your face.
Maybe you should cut it?
Shut up!
Why don't you want to?
None of your business, okay?
Yeah, well, at least you
have long hair to cut.
[KANDA]
Huh?
[ALLEN] Great, you made
her cry, you big jerk!