Barba!
Allen!
O... Okay... alright...
Just tell me what's wrong...
Calm down, buddy!
Allen, are you okay?
I'm fine...
At least... I think so.
Barba...
What happened that
got you so upset?
Lenny.
Poor Liza...
She loved Lenny so much.
When I think about it,
it makes me cry.
Oh no... Where is Liza?
They still haven't
cleared out this room yet?
Didn't I tell you to
get Lenny's stuff...
So you can clean up the mess
in this room, we need the bed.
You can't trust
anyone these days.
Hey what are you doing in there?
Me?
I thought that was you...
Don't you know
better than to wander
into another patient's
room without authorization?
I'm so sorry.
It's hard enough doing this job
without having to
baby-sit all the trainees.
Trainees?
But, but I...
You were instructed,
just like all the others,
to find me, the Head Nurse,
as soon as you arrived
How do you expect to work here
if you can't even do that?
Please, hold on a second, Miss.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
This hospital's
so big I got lost.
It won't happen
again. I promise.
Look, we need to get going.
We're shorthanded today and
need all the help we can get.
What'd she get into?
Well...
I'm not worried about it...
I'm sure Lenalee can
handle herself just fine...
Liza?
Liza, have you had a chance
to think about what
we discussed earlier?
I want you to be
back on your feet,
but in order to do that,
we need to act soon.
That's why I still
believe the method
I proposed is our best option.
What is he talking about?
Hello?
Oh, I apologize, hello...
Allen!
You know this boy?
Yes...
I met him through Mother, the
woman who's been helping me.
Mother...? Ahh...
right, I see now.
She's the old woman
you've been seeking
advice from lately...
Yes, that's her.
I'm currently...
Mother's acting apprentice.
And what are you doing here?
I heard Lenny passed away
so I came by to pay my respects.
His funeral will
be held tomorrow...
Now I'd prefer it if Liza
were left alone for awhile...
You do understand, don't you?
Yes... but...
Please son, just leave.
If you're worried about
Liza the best thing
you can do for her
is go home, okay?
No, no. It's alright.
Huh?
I don't mind it...
Will you stay...? Please, Allen?
Oh, of course.
Okay...
He can stay if
that's what you want.
Thank you Director...
I appreciate it.
Just promise me
you'll think about
what we discussed earlier.
It's important, Liza.
I'll need to know
your answer soon.
Sure.
So Liza...
What was that about?
He's trying to get me
to take some counseling.
Ahh... counseling?
He said losing Lenny
is a major trauma,
and to heal that hole in
my heart I'll need help.
You're still not finished?
You forgot these...
Get rid of them.
I grew those flowers myself!
I'm not going to
throw them away!
I don't care...
Just get them out of here, now.
I'm sorry... Barba.
Does Doctor Robert always
treat people that way?
No, but he's been in a
really bad mood lately.
Oh...
I think it has something to do
with some loan shark
he hasn't paid back yet.
Is that right?
I know, I know.
I will pay you back soon...
I just need some more time...
Whatever you do, do not come
to the hospital, you understand?
Oh wait...
I wonder if Allen and
Lenalee are coming back.
Hey Mother!
Are Allen and Lenalee
coming back tonight?
Do you think I should
make food for them too?
Well, you must be tired,
being your first day and all.
Yeah... Though you seem okay.
How long have you been here?
For the better part
of two years now...
Not too long after this hospital
was built I relocated
here from a village nearby.
So this hospital's
only two years old?
Yep...
You should have seen it
when it was first built.
It wasn't nearly this big.
Ever since the renovations
were completed six months ago,
our number of patients
has skyrocketed.
Six months...
I do know the number
of Akuma has gone up
significantly over
the past six months.
Seems most of our patients
are terminally ill...
The Director
treats them for free
so we're pretty much
packed all the time.
I'd be surprised if this
place made any money.
Around the time
the hospital expanded,
they began taking
terminal patients,
which is the same time
Akuma started showing up.
Is the Director behind
this in some way?
If so, what would
be his motive...?
Or is Robert using
the Director's goodwill,
to funnel grieving relatives
to the Millennium Earl
in exchange for money?
No matter who's behind it,
someone in this hospital
is actually brokering
souls for the Earl.
At first he only had
slight pneumonia...
The doctors told us he would be
released in about
a week or so...
But no matter what they did,
he wouldn't get any better...
From that point on I started
believing it was my fault,
because I wasn't good
enough at caring for him.
But Lenny didn't actually
believe that, did he?
I'm sure he told you
it wasn't your fault.
Yeah...
He was always smiling,
trying to encourage me.
It wasn't long after
when he told me
he was starting to
have feelings for me...
Which was great, because
I was attracted to him,
especially his smile.
But then, just days after
we said "I love you"
to each other
for the first time,
the Director told
us the bad news.
He had diagnosed Lenny
with a terminal illness...
Of course Lenny
was upset about it,
but he accepted his fate and
took everything in stride...
He was so calm, when anyone else
in that position would have
been a wreck finding out
they only had weeks to live...
Instead, Lenny was more
worried about me than himself.
I'm sorry...
but I can't stop crying.
Allen?
When you need to cry it's
better to just let it go.
When I lost someone
very dear to me
I cried my eyes out for days...
No wait...
It was actually a
lot longer than that...
It was more like a few weeks.
You lost someone?
Who?
Mana...
He was my foster father.
So how did you get on with
your life after losing him?
How did you get
over the empty feeling
in the pit of your heart?
Even now it's really tough
for me to talk about Mana,
but I still rely on him
for emotional support
even though he's gone.
I can get by each day because of
all the wonderful memories I
have of him when he was alive.
As long as I don't
forget about him...
Mana will continue
to live inside me
for the rest of my life.
You're right...
That's nice...
and it makes sense.
Lenny will live
inside me as long as...
I don't forget.
Yes... that's it...
You'll be okay...
Hey, was that...
Yes, I have another
one set up for you,
just as I promised.
What?
I don't understand.
I put the wrong day
on my calendar.
I was supposed
to start yesterday
but I wrote down today...
I'm so sorry.
Then who is that other girl?
Where did he get
the funds to renovate
the hospital when he isn't
charging patients for treatment?
If I can find out where
the money's coming from...
The Director
financed it himself?
Where in the world is he
getting that kind of money...?
That must mean the broker is...
You shouldn't be
sticking your nose
in other people's business.
I know you're not a nurse
like you say you are,
so who the hell are you...?
Get back here!
They already have you working
so soon after the funeral...?
I guess that must
be pretty tough...
Are you gonna be okay?
I'll be fine...
Besides I'd rather
have something to do
to help me get my
mind off of things.
Just don't push
yourself too hard.
Thanks for looking out
for me you guys, really...
Oh right, I almost
forgot about this.
Mother asked me to give
you this envelope, here.
That's for me?
Hold it!
If you don't stop,
I'm gonna have you
arrested for trespassing!
I don't have time
to deal with this guy,
not when Liza's in danger!
I thought I'd find you up here.
I've been looking for you, Liza.
Oh, hello Director.
You poor thing,
you must be a wreck.
Here, Liza...
Come with me and we'll sit
down and talk through this.
Trust me, it will
help you grieve.
I can't. I have work to do.
Forget about work...
You need help.
Damn it, she's fast.
I can't even
keep up with her!
Move it!
How could you do that?!
Lenalee?
What the hell is that thing?
It's an Akuma,
we're not safe here...
Akuma?
Allen!
No... no... no!
This entire hospital is like
some Akuma manufacturing plant.
There's someone
working in this hospital
that sold his soul to
the Millennium Earl...
And these poor people
have become his victims.
Now let's save their souls
from any more torment!
You and Lenny shared a bond
that could only
be broken by death.
Wouldn't you like to be
with him once again?
If you act now I can make
that happen for you...
You're one of the lucky ones...
Think about it, you can
hear his voice once again,
and see that smile
you loved so much.
Lenny wants to see you again.
He is dying to, and
you can make it happen.
He wants to... to see me?
He does...
He wants you more than
anything else in the world.
It was his dying wish,
and you can make
it come true for him
if you just give
me your permission.
Allen, the hospital's
Director is the broker.
Broker?
He's been using dying
patients as bait for the Earl,
so they can be Akuma...
The Director's building
an army for the Earl...
He's even making
money off of it...
Since I found out
he had money problems
I've been suspicious
of Robert...
But he was shocked at
the sight of an Akuma.
Leaving the Director
as our best suspect.
Let's hurry...
We have to stop him before
he creates any more Akuma.
The door's locked.
Your things are
already prepared.
All I need to do is set up
an appointment for you,
and then once that is made,
the only thing you will have
to do is call his soul back.
It will be very easy.
Call his soul back?
I was afraid this
was going to happen!
I'll handle all the details,
but all you'll need
to do is say his name
and he will literally
come back to life.
Well...? Aren't
you excited Liza?
I am... I want to
see him so badly.
Oh... So you've decided!
Fantastic...! You've
made the right decision...
Good girl...
I'll go make the call.
I want to see him... but I...
I don't need him to
come back to life.
'Scuse me?
It's because... he already
lives in my heart.
That nonsense isn't
going to help anyone.
Liza open up!
Liza!
I'm sick of this hymning
and hawing from you.
Forget about your consent.
We're going through this
whether you want to or not.
What are you doing?
You have no idea who
you're dealing with.
This is not the kind of
person you make wait.
You forced my hand, Liza.
Sarah was an easy one,
while you two took
more time and effort.
The poison I was feeding
Lenny worked perfectly,
prolonging his illness
long enough to get you both
to fall in love just
like I had planned.
I've worked too long on this,
to let you walk away.
Who's there?!
Identify yourself!
I am an Exorcist...
I destroy Akuma... and
save souls from torment...
The Millennium Earl
is our enemy.
You're trying to
stop the Earl...
Right...
I thought you'd like to know
we destroyed all your Akuma.
Let me guess...
You're an Exorcist too?
You're a soul broker,
aren't you...?
You've been collaborating
with the Earl
by using your patients
as bait for his army...
and turning a nice
profit while you're at it.
What drives a man
to do such a thing...?
Especially since
you're... human.
Stay where you are.
You want to know why I did it.
I did it for the
people living here...
The people of this town...
What do you mean?
The only chance a
rat hole in the middle
of nowhere has for developing
is by opening a hospital
and filling it with patients,
otherwise it will die.
All I ever did,
I did for this town.
That's enough!
Mother!
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you two
so I called Mother
here to save the day...
She's so tough anytime she's
in the room there's
no need to worry.
Is that right?
You know she does
seem to have gotten
much stronger over
the last three years.
I can't believe she
knocked him out in one shot.
Oh, I'm not finished...
I'll make certain he atones for
his sins against humanity...
It will be up to us to show him
what a terrible mistake he made,
by putting all those
souls in danger.
You two should never forget
what you saw here today.
The Earl doesn't just
turn humans into Akuma...
He manipulates their desires
and uses their minds to
turn them into collaborators,
forcing them to do his bidding
through blackmail or slavery.
Right.
It will be a tough fight,
but don't forget that not
all humans are weak enough
to fall under his spell,
like Liza here.
Through it all, she never
lost her strength or will,
even when the odds
were stacked against her.
Hello hello...?
Well no kidding, huh...
I'll be over right away...
It's no big deal to
lose a collaborator
or two now and then...
Luckily for me there are
countless other people
who are willing to give their
effort towards the cause.
I'm not as strong as
I've been made out to be...
There are many times
I thought I would crack,
but this letter
that Mother gave me
really helped me through it.
"There is no sense
in you being sad just
because I'm no longer there,
for I will always
be by your side.
Any time you want to see me,
just think back on all
the wonderful memories.
Don't be sad, my dear Liza.
Live your life to the
fullest and never look back...
For as long as I can, I will
pray for your happiness."
Liza has a full
life ahead of her.
It'll be nice having
Lenny at her side.
Yes... For sure.
There's another
letter I forgot about.
Huh...?
But Liza just left.
You better grab her
before she's gone.
Not her...
It's addressed to Lenalee...
It arrived at Mother's
house just a few hours ago.
I'm not expecting anything.
It's from my brother.
Come back to Headquarters
double, triple, quadruple quick!
I really really need
you here, Lenalee!
It's urgent!
Come...! Come back...!
Hurry up and come
back protisimo...
Something fishy's going on.
That's strange...
He didn't even
mention my name once.
What now...?
Do you wanna head back
with me to Headquarters?
But I still haven't been
able to find Master Cross...
These are for you.
Wow... I guess I've
become pretty popular, huh?
What...?
They're just a bunch of
overdue bills address to Master!
Those letters can help
you find Master Cross...
Just trace back
the return addresses
and you'll find where he's been.
What do you say we
give it a shot, Timcanpy?
Miranda was making her way
to the Black Order
to become an Exorcist,
when she accidentally
got lost...!
Now she's faced with
two different paths...
Which one does she choose,
and then what happens?
On the next D. Gray-man:
"Lost Miranda."
Bring forth salvation to
this tormented Akuma's soul.