Begone, Akuma!
John...
I know you mean well
but you've got to stop this.
Leo's been dead for some time...
He died on the day of
his mommy's funeral.
Leo, no...
Allen?!
With the Earl's power,
Leo was able to bring his
mother's soul back
from death to this world...
and she was turned...
into an Akuma.
Ahhh, I remember you now...!
Yes, indeed-d, I met you a
long time ago, didn't I...?
Your name is Allen
Walker, isn't it...?
Aren't you the little
brat who wanted me
to bring his dead
daddy back to life?
Did Allen turn his own
father into an Akuma?!
Allen's father...
He made him... an Akuma?
No. Mana wasn't my
real father, John.
I had been abandoned...
for being born with
this strange arm...
and Mana, he was the
one who took me in...
He wasn't afraid of my arm
and he helped raise me.
Never stop...
Keep walking.
You see...
Mana was the only one
who taught me about living...
What you need to have to live...
and how to take care
of myself in the world.
But...
when he disappeared and
I was suddenly all by myself...
I didn't know...
I couldn't remember how
to take care of me anymore.
I never really
believed that Mana...
that Father could die...
Mana... come on...
Wake up, Mana!
Mana!
Allen... listen to me...
No matter what happens...
No matter what...
Never stop...
Don't talk like that...
Please, Mana, get up!
Never stop...
Always keep walking...
I need you.
Don't leave me alone!
Always keep walking, Allen!
Until the day... you die...
No...
Mana...
Wake up...
Please don't go...
Don't die and leave me...
Mana!
Good evening,
little one. You look sad...
Huh?
Would you like me to bring your
daddy back to life for you?
What?
I simply need
you to call for him,
since you have such
a special bond...
Wouldn't it be great if
you could see him again?
He'll come back?
Of course...
Come, let's call him back
from your detestable God.
But can he...
I mean, will he...
hear me calling?
Now... raise your voice
and call the soul
of the one you love
back from the other world.
That's it...
Don't be scared now...
Mana!!
Mana!
Al... Allen.
How could you...?
How dare you make me an Akuma!
I curse you... Allen!
How could you make me an Akuma?!
Oh, young Allen,
you're all mine now...
Mana Walker, I order you to
kill the boy and wear his body!
I curse you... Allen!
I didn't know what
had happened...
My left arm
somehow activated...
and moved on it's own...
it attacked the Akuma
holding Mana's soul.
Stop... Don't hurt Mana!
Run, Father...
Father... no!
Allen...
I love you.
Destroy Me...
Please...
Destroy me...
Allen.
Mana!!!
Then Master came...
and explained it to me...
Everything that
happened that day.
Everything...
What made up an Akuma,
all about the evil
Millennium Earl, and even...
what had happened to me.
Does he mean General Cross...?
But how did he...
The souls trapped inside
Akuma are powerless...
They're forever captive...
and become dangerous
toys of the Millennium Earl.
Destroying them is the
only way to save them.
A human born with an
Anti-Akuma Weapon...
What an unfortunate fate.
You also appear to be an
apostle possessed by God.
How would you like to
be... an Exorcist?
Ever since that time...
I've been able to see the souls
trapped inside
The Earl's Akumas.
At first...
I thought Mana was
cursing me out of anger...
so I tried to be an
Exorcist to atone
for what I'd done to him...
but as I began to encounter many
Akuma, I realized something...
They don't shed tears
out of hatred...
but of deepest love
they feel toward those
who turned them into Akuma.
They weep knowing that we
could never bear the pain.
I discovered that my fate
was to be an Exorcist...
not to atone for sin, but to
live true to my calling here.
And this cursed Weapon...
has been a faithful guide.
Akuma are tragic creatures...
They shouldn't have to
suffer in this existence.
And therefore...
I destroy them.
Allen Walker...
I should have
killed you long ago.
You can see the
souls inside Akuma...?
You want to save 'em...?
Go ahead, Exorcist...
I want to see you try.
Take your best shot,
but let me go first!
No!
Allen, lookout!
Don't worry about me...
I took the bullets earlier...
because I had to protect John...
but with this level of attack...
they can't kill me.
Allen...
The virus didn't work,
so you think you can
just shoot me to death...?
Don't underestimate me.
You see, whenever
the Anti-Akuma Weapon
is activated within me...
it exhibits superhuman strength
and incredible speed...
The Akuma's bullets
and hard exteriors
are no match for this arm.
It is God's weapon...
and it exists for the sole
purpose of destroying yours.
What conceit...
Well, then...
Lero, lero, lero!
Tell me, do you know the
old Eastern proverb...?
He who fires in the
end shall hit the mark.
And with bullets like these...
How can I miss?!
Now...
Akuma cannons... fire!
Allen...!
Allen!!
And you... you will die!
Innocence... activate!
Lenalee?!
Watch out for him!
That's amazing...
Lenalee is an Exorcist!
I had no idea...
She has an
Anti-Akuma Weapon, too?
Yes...
Hers fly in the sky
like butterflies...
and yet come down as powerful
and destructive as steel.
Lenalee's Anti-Akuma
weapon is known as...
the Dark Boots.
Incredible!
Ah, so another insect has
appeared in the sky...
This ought to be fun.
In no time at all you'll
be dead as well, girl!
Just look at them, hopping
all over the place...
Make them disappear!
No, Lenalee!
Are you alright?!
Uh-huh... yeah, I'm okay.
Perfect. You can die together!
The Akuma must be
destroyed soon...
or this entire town
will be at great risk!
Destroyed...
Akuma are evil, malicious
weapons created by the Earl...
the Enemy of mankind...
They have to be destroyed...
I thought... I knew
what we were doing...
Listen to this, Leo...!
It says that Akuma wear the
skin of the humans they kill!
But if that's true
then how could we tell
if someone was an Akuma or not?
I was the one who
told Leo about Akuma...
and I made him go
on patrol with me...
Leo, you knew the
Millennium Earl was evil...
You knew it...!
So how...
how could you...
Were you so shocked by your
mother's death that you forgot?
Was the pain too hard for you?
Mother!
Stupid...
You're so stupid...
Did you miss her so much that
you had to do this to her...?!
Use him to make
her into an Akuma?!
I don't have Allen's eye...
and I can't see
an Akuma's soul...
I don't know if Leo's mother is
really crying in there or not!
I can't see...
...but it's awful!
I'm sorry... Leo.
The Akuma are so strong...
All of them have
to be destroyed...
I thought they were just
fun things to talk about.
I never thought about
what they really are--
that they're real people
who are suffering.
The people whose souls
are made into Akuma
are never free again.
They... They all become...
the Millennium Earl's toys...
forever.
Akuma are tragic creatures...
They shouldn't have to
suffer in this existence.
And therefore...
I destroy them.
Allen, destroy him...!
Destroy Leo!
Please... release him
from his suffering!
With this one blow...
I'll send them all to the grave.
I will be your salvation...
Cross...
Grave!
This is not good, lero...!
Level one Akuma are no
match for this one, lero!
We will take our
leave for now...
but make no mistake,
I'll be back!
Earl!!
Oh yes, these exciting exercises
have merely been
a prelude, my boy...
Akuma are continuing to
evolve all over the globe...
and the groundwork
is being laid'
for an end of the
world spectacular.
Behold...
I am the Millennium Earl...
the Maker of Akuma...
the one who will defeat your
disgraced and powerless God...
and destroy this pathetic
world with my weapons.
No matter how hard you
Exorcists strive and struggle...
you will never be able
to save yourselves...
Never!
We'll see... next time...
Allen!
You okay?
I'm alright...
I think...
I'm just a little
bit tired, that's all.
John?
I just...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Allen...
Lenalee, where were you??!
Oh, how you could you stay out
all night without telling me?
John sent it?
Well, yes... but listen,
you should probably be
careful when you open it.
I missed you so very much...
That's one stinky bomb...
If this onion toy
is the best he can do
then he's still got
a long way to go.
Funny, that's
what John said, too.
I want to go work
with my dad someday...
I'll study more
and improve myself...
since it seems like there's so
much I don't understand yet...
So please tell him
to wait for me
until I get there, okay, Allen?
Alright...
Well, let's both do our best.
Is he crying?!
Sure looks like it.
Well, there's something
you don't see every day.
Quiet...!
I got onion in my eye...
it hurts!
You've still got a lot to
learn as well... don't you?
Eh?
I wasn't aware that
The Order began
allowing Exorcists to act
on their own like that...
But still...
my son was saved
thanks to you, Walker.
What do you say...
let's try to finish this
portion off quickly...
I think I need to take
a few days' vacation...
to go visit my son.
That's a great idea!
Well, it doesn't
seem terribly fair
that you're the only one
to get a good scolding...
I've got a little bit
left for him as well.
Never stop...
Keep walking...
Mana.
Every exorcist and scientist
at the Black Order is exhausted
from working day and night...
And Komui puts more
pressure on us all.
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"The Black Order
Annihilation Incident"?!
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul!