[ROAD] Take a step
and everyone dies.
Surely you remember what my
candles did to your left eye.
That was a sample of
the pain they can inflict.
You wouldn't
want your friends,
especially sweet,
adorable Lenalee,
to be turned into human
pincushions, would you?
Then do as I say and stay
still until I break Lavi.
[ALLEN gasps]
[ZOMBIES moan]
Lavi... Lavi...
[LAVI]
Shut up!
[ZOMBIES moan]
[LAVI]
Don't look.
[REEVER]
Lavi.
[LAVI]
Don't look.
[ZOMBIES moan]
[LAVI] It'll only
make me more confused.
[ZOMBIES moan]
Lavi... Lavi...
Lavi, why?
Tell us why, Lavi.
[ZOMBIES moan]
[ZOMBIES yell]
[LAVI]
It's just an illusion.
[ZOMBIES yell]
[KOMUI] What do you
think you're doing?
Damn!
[ZOMBIE groans]
[LENALEE]
You've abandoned us.
We're your comrades.
How could you do this to us?
[LAVI] Don't.
Don't listen to them!
They're not really there!
[ZOMBIES moan]
[LAVI grunts]
[ZOMBIES groan]
[LAVI] They're not real.
Don't let yourself forget that!
[LAVI] I have to get
out of here, now!
[BOOKMAN] I hereby accept
you as the successor
to the title of Bookman.
[LAVI gasps]
[BOOKMAN] The secret history
we witness and gather
is the complete collection
of all historical facts
that are omitted from
mankind's records.
[BOOKMAN] From now on,
it's your responsibility
to write them down.
Understand?
[SMALL LAVI]
Right.
[SMALL LAVI gasps]
[SMALL LAVI] This way
I can learn things
that no one else knows.
That's why I can't
wait to be a Bookman.
Stop it!
[LAVI] Someone's looking
into my memories!
[SMALL LAVI gasps]
[LAVI] Wherever we went, it was
just one war after another.
In my time as a Bookman, I've
witnessed a total of 48 wars.
It boggles my mind
how stupid people are.
Just killing each other
time and time again.
I get so sick of watching
them screw things up.
[BOOKMAN]
Mm.
But this time won't be
like the other wars.
We'll disguise
ourselves as soldiers
and observe from
their perspective.
You're inexperienced, so listen
carefully to what I tell you.
No matter what position
we find ourselves in,
it will always be a
Bookman's duty to--
To record history and
nothing more than that.
We're never to interfere
with other people.
You see?
I understand it.
All I can do is smile and
laugh and go with the flow.
[BOOKMAN sighs]
[BOOKMAN] Just try to stay out
of trouble, would you, Deek?
Hey, "Deek" was my
48th name, remember?
It's Lavi now,
so just call me that.
That's good to hear.
[REEVER] Thank you for waiting.
Our chief is ready to see you.
I welcome you to the
Black Order, gentlemen.
Science Section Chief
Komui Lee.
[BOOKMAN]
I don't have a name,
so I would prefer for you
to call me Bookman.
[LAVI] Coffins.
Is this a funeral?
[BOOKMAN] That young man there
is Lavi, my successor.
[LAVI] They must be
on the losing side.
[LAVI gasps]
[LENALEE weeps]
Stop, that's enough already!
[REEVER]
Lavi.
[JOHNNY]
No!
You wanna measure me? Can't you
just eyeball it or something?
Come on, don't be ridiculous!
A well-fitting coat
can do wonders for an
Exorcist's defense, you know!
On top of that,
it improves your mobility!
Johnny, give
the guy some space!
Hey! Section leader!
You think Lavi would look good
in a long coat like Kanda's,
or keep it short? Huh?
Wow, he is really
into this, huh?
You're one of us now,
so they wanna
make sure you're protected.
Let's measure.
[LAVI] I wonder if these
people are gonna be
left out of history one day?
[LAVI pants]
And so you stayed
at the Order.
What was it, two years you were
there? And during that time,
you became increasingly
close to the people you met.
[OTHER LAVI] Despite your
responsibility as a Bookman
to remain impartial, you began
to consider them your comrades.
[LAVI]
Shut up!
[OTHER LAVI]
You must be confused.
You can't even determine
whether that smile of yours
is real or fake anymore,
can you, Lavi?
[LAVI] I said stop!
Stop! Leave me alone!
[LAVI shudders]
[LAVI gasps]
[ALLEN]
Hey, I lost this.
So you held onto it
all this time,
and without
telling Bookman.
Allen.
[OTHER LAVI]
Fire Stamp.
[ALLEN screams]
Allen!
[LAVI gasps]
Aw, what's all this about?
You look like your
heart's shattering.
[splash]
[LAVI shudders]
Oh, come on. A Bookman
doesn't need comrades.
That's what the
rules say, you know?
Ya can't go and let
yourself get attached.
It's only bound to cause
you pain in the end.
And if you do feel
that way about someone,
the best thing you
can do is destroy them.
You know that, don't you?
Oh, are there more?
And looky here. You better
get your knife ready.
Why are you hesitating?
Go on, cut them down already.
[ALLEN]
Lavi...
[LAVI shudders]
[ALLEN]
Lavi...
[LAVI pants]
[LAVI coughs, retches]
[OTHER LAVI chuckles]
You never had what it takes
to be a Bookman. Pathetic.
Why can't you
kill your comrades?
It really shouldn't be
that difficult for you.
[OTHER LAVI]
Don't worry.
The Bookman line will
live on, even if you die.
I'll take your place
as the next Bookman.
So you can disappear now.
[ROAD] Looks like I
just broke Lavi's mind.
[ROAD laughs]
Still, no matter what happens
in my world of dreams,
he can't actually be
hurt by illusions.
His friends only
stabbed him in his mind,
not out here in reality.
But the shock of being
done in by his own comrades
caused him to lose his sanity.
While his body is alive,
his mind is dead.
But there is something left
behind that I can use.
[ROAD]
Now. Come out.
[ROAD] It's time for
you to be set free.
[LENALEE gasps]
L... Lavi?
Sort of. If you want to save
Lenalee and that human,
you're going to
have to beat that.
[LENALEE gasps]
Lavi!
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN yells]
No way. Why is he attacking
me all of a sudden?
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN screams]
[ALLEN] There's gotta be
something bad possessing him!
[ALLEN] If it's evil, my sword
should be able to exorcise it!
Come on, please work!
[ALLEN groans]
Don't bother with
the sword of exorcism,
'cause it's not evil
that's controlling him!
Attack with Edge on
your left arm instead!
Tear him into tiny pieces! It's
the only way you can stop him!
[LENALEE] You know he
can't do that, Road!
[ROAD chuckles]
[ROAD] You'd better hurry up
and use Edge, Allen.
Or I'll kill them right now!
You're not being fair!
[LENALEE] She knows
it's impossible for Allen
to do that voluntarily.
Switch out your weapon!
Unless you want to watch
Lenalee die, of course!
[ALLEN groans]
[ALLEN coughs]
[ALLEN] Lavi. You can
hear my voice, can't you?
You and I... We're
the only people left
who can protect Lenalee
and Chaozii now.
Krory said so, remember?
Kanda would say the same.
[ALLEN groans]
Stop it.
[ALLEN coughs]
For Lenalee...
...her comrades...
are more important
than anything else
in this entire world.
You're gonna make her cry!
Comrades, huh?
You think so? I don't.
[ALLEN grunts]
[ALLEN yells]
[ALLEN groans]
[LENALEE shudders]
[LENALEE]
Please stop!
[LERO]
Ah!
Haven't you gotten it
through your skull yet?
[ROAD] This is how
Lavi really feels!
I've never once thought of
any of you as my comrades.
I'm Lavi, the sole successor
to Bookman. Nothing else.
And I don't need you.
[ALLEN grunts]
[LAVI]
Devouring Flame.
Fire Stamp!
[ALLEN]
Crown Clown!
It split in two!
[ALLEN] This sword's
ability is exorcism,
so it's useless against the
power of Lavi's Innocence.
My only option is to change
to Crown Clown's Edge.
[ALLEN gasps]
But I can't! If I use that,
it'll hurt Lavi too!
There has to be another way!
What do I do?
[LAVI]
Heaven Stamp.
[LENALEE] Lavi!
Please stop attacking him!
Snap out of it, now!
Nyeh. You're just
wasting your breath.
It's no use! Lavi's mind
has been destroyed.
All that's left
is a Bookman.
The way he's acting right now
is the way he really is.
He doesn't have any friends.
Not you or anyone else.
[LAVI]
Devouring Flame.
Lavi...
[ALLEN] I don't know
if Road's doing this,
so I'll just have to guess!
[LERO screams]
Mistress Road!
[ROAD laughs]
[ROAD] Aw, too bad! You
guessed wrong. I have to
give you credit for thinking
outside the box, though.
Your attacks are as
useless as they were
back in that rewinding town.
Did you forget about that?
[ROAD] Who cares
what this sword can do
if you're not really hitting me?
Here's the thing. I'm me,
but I'm not actually me.
Come on. If you don't
know anything about me,
then how are you
ever gonna beat me?
[ALLEN]
No...
[ROAD] Why don't you just
do what I tell you to do?
You're a decent Exorcist,
but even you
can't control how people feel.
Fire Stamp!
Now surrender!
[ALLEN screams]
Oh, Allen! Please, no!
Stop this, Lavi!
Call off the flames!
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN] I'm surrounded by fire,
but it doesn't burn.
[LENALEE]
Lavi! I'm begging you!
[LENALEE] The heat's
causing them to melt.
[ALLEN] That's so weird...
Why am I not burning up?
[LENALEE gasps]
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALLEN]
Whoa.
Wait, huh? My body is...
...moving on its own!
Impossible!
[LAVI] Apparently it
is possible, jackass.
How dare you go out
of control like this?
Agh, it hurts.
Have you lost your mind?
Lost my mind?
Funny you should say that.
[LAVI groans]
[OTHER LAVI gasps]
[LAVI]
That was close.
If your mind is broken, you're
supposed to go insane, right?
[LAVI] In that moment,
when they attacked me,
I did what I had to do
to protect my sanity.
[LAVI]
Now that that's over.
I'm going to make sure you pay
dearly for playing with my mind.
What the...?
And I'm not holding back!
Fire Stamp!
Lavi!
[ALLEN]
No!
Lavi, wait!
[LERO screams]
She's been swallowed up
by the flames, lero!
[ROAD] He's insane.
Why would a Bookman
let himself be
burned to a crisp?
It may be noble,
but it won't actually--
[ROAD gasps]
[LAVI]
Too real for you?
Then how about an attack from
that dream world of yours?
I didn't give you
enough credit.
[ROAD] I'm impressed you
figured out my disguise.
Well, of course. You do seem to
have a thing for Allen, so...
[ROAD chuckles]
[ROAD] It's over. You'll never
become the next Bookman.
Heh. It looks like you've
backed me into a corner.
[LAVI] I didn't
want to do this,
but it's my best
course of action.
[LAVI]
I'm sorry.
This is goodbye.
[ALLEN] After aiming
Fire Stamp at himself,
Lavi is becoming
engulfed in hellfire.
Lenalee and I
call out his name,
but will our voices be
able to reach him?
On the next D. Gray-man,
"Voice of Darkness."
Bring forth salvation
to this poor Akuma's soul!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[LAVI]
Huh? Oh--!
Uh, Lavi, are you
hiding something?
Uh... What? Of course not!
[ALLEN screams]
Hey, who said you could
eat all my snacks?
Aah! I didn't eat all of 'em!
[ALLEN growls]
Jeez, you two! What's with
the racket in here?
[ALLEN, LAVI grunt]
[ALLEN, LAVI chuckle]