[FO groaning]
Bak.
Fo?
Bak...
Bak!
Hide Walker before
it breaks through!
Bak!
[AKUMA A laughs] So you're the
entrance to the barrier, huh?
There's no way!
How did an Akuma manage to get
through the seal so easily?
It's impossible!
[AKUMA A] Actually, it
required very little effort.
[AKUMA A] My passage here was
granted courtesy of Noah's Ark.
[ALLEN gasps]
[AKUMA A]
A boy with gray hair,
and a strange left eye.
You wouldn't be the
infamous Allen Walker?
Would you?
[ALLEN grunts]
[FO groaning]
[screams] That thing!
It came out of Fo's body!
[SHIFU]
My guess is it's an Akuma.
Idiot! Everyone here
knows it's an Akuma!
The issue is that seal has been
protecting the Asia Branch
for over a hundred years!
How did it manage to break
through just like that?
Even more importantly,
how did it know exactly
where to find Allen?
[ALLEN]
Wait a minute...
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
I know that butterfly!
[FO]
Walker...
Run away... Go!
This Akuma has only one goal.
To kill you.
The shape you're in,
there's no way you can win.
Get outta here!
I'm not running!
[AKUMA A]
I won't allow you to run!
[screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[LI KEI]
Walker!
[LO FWA]
What is that thing?
[FO gasping]
He's still alive! Hang in there.
It pierced right
through his body!
What is this?
A string?
[AKUMA A]
My dark matter has the power
to disintegrate
all other matter.
That thread breaks
down and absorbs
whatever it passes through
until there's nothing left.
Now, boy. It's time
for you to disappear...
...forever!
[ALLEN screams]
Walker!
[AKUMA A] My orders from the
Noah were to bring you back
if I found you still alive.
But they never specified that
you had to remain that way.
I will present them with
your molecules as a trophy.
He's fading!
Walker's starting to disappear!
Dammit! How do I cut this
thread? What do we do?
Stop it.
You hear me?! Don't disappear!
Houshin.
I summon you!
By my blood, I command
you to attack!
[gasps]
Director Bak!
Now, Fo! This is our chance!
Finally. You idiot.
Get Allen out of here!
My attack will hold him back,
but only for so long.
[ALL whimpering]
[BAK]
One more time.
I command you!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Alert!
An Akuma has infiltrated
the facility!
Location, central North Sector.
I repeat!
An Akuma has infiltrated
the facility!
The north district
will be on lockdown
after staff evacuation!
We are switching to high alert!
[STAFF screaming]
[ANNOUNCER A] If you're located
in the northern direction,
do not panic! Please act
in a calm manner!
Follow your section leader's
evacuation instructions!
[STAFF screaming, chattering]
[LI KEI] It's seriously
getting bad down there!
Complete chaos!
What do we do, Chief?
[gasps] Look at Allen!
He's almost invisible!
What do you...?
Lo Fwa's right!
What's wrong with him?
Why is he vanishing?
Dammit! It looks
like that attack
did more damage than
I originally thought.
Uh?
Whatever you do,
don't jostle him.
Now Listen to me
carefully, Li Kei.
That Akuma's ability
seriously damaged Allen.
To the point where it made his
molecular structure unstable.
His life is literally
in your hands.
He can't get hit even once,
or he may break down
to the molecular level.
[LO FWA]
What?
You're shaking him too much!
And don't you dare drop him!
[SHIFU]
His life is in your hands!
[inaudible]
That Akuma...
He looked different.
[BAK] You've never seen
a Level Three before?
That was a Level Three?
They're something.
Nothing like the Level Two's.
Their strength and abilities
are in another league.
I've only read about them
in the Order's archive files.
This will be my first
time fighting one.
[ALLEN exhales]
[STAFF chattering, screaming]
[WONG]
Chief Bak!
[BAK]
Wong!
[WONG] All the staff have
evacuated the northern sector
and moved to this side
of the facility.
Good work.
And the other thing?
Everything's ready to go
just the way you asked.
Fo.
Hey, Fo!
[FO]
You don't have to shout.
I can hear you fine.
You idiot.
I'm sorry Fo.
But I have to ask you
to do the impossible.
Ha. Like always.
[BAK] All right!
Let's hurry up and move.
[ALL panting]
[LI KEI]
Wait up, Chief!
What's the plan?
[BAK] We'll run to
the end of the hall,
then I'll seal off
this district!
[LO FWA]
What?!
[SHIFU]
You're just gonna abandon it?
[BAK]
There's no other options!
We don't have any Exorcists
who can fight Akuma.
We have to cut off
this district,
or else we'll face
total destruction!
[ALL panting]
[LO FWA] You're gonna
block the passage?!
[SHIFU]
How is that possible, Director?
With the blood that flows
through my veins!
Passed down by my
great-grandfather,
the Chang family has the power
to control the guardian
deities of this facility!
Come forth,
by order of my blood!
Seal it off!
[ALL scream]
[LI KEI]
The rocks are coming to life!
[BAK] Come on...
There's not much time.
[crashing]
[AKUMA A] These humans are
just delaying the inevitable.
[AKUMA A chuckles]
They think that'll stop me?
Fo!
[FO groaning]
I've got you...
...Walker...
Hang in there, okay?
You know what? Despite
appearances, you got guts.
Even if you're just a kid.
[ALLEN gasps]
You'll reactivate your
Innocence one day.
I'm sure of it.
Your face... Why did you...
[FO laughs]
But Fo, you're injured!
You can't fight him!
Fo!
I'm no Exorcist, Allen.
Just a guardian deity
with zero expectations
of defeating him at all.
[ALLEN gasping]
[FO]
But hopefully,
I can buy you some time.
You better run.
Ah! Don't go!
Let me go! I'll fight
the Akuma instead!
Bak! Stop her!
Let me go in her place! No!
Well then. You finally decided
to accept your fate.
Too bad.
I was looking forward
to hunting you.
I am Allen Walker, and I won't
let you pass any further.
We'll see about that.
Stop her! Let me through!
[ALLEN]
Fo!
[AKUMA A]
You willingly return
after how easily I put
you down the first time?
You're either brave
or incredibly stupid.
Regardless, this
shouldn't take long.
You're move, Allen Walker.
Good bye... Bak.
[AKUMA A grunts]
[FO yells]
[AKUMA A chuckles]
[FO yelling]
This is so boring.
[FO gasping]
[FO screams]
[sighs]
Hm?
[AKUMA A] That's the spirit
I was hoping for.
I would've been disappointed
if killing you were that easy.
An absolute waste of my time.
You agree, Allen Walker?
I won't make it easy for you.
Open this wall right now, Bak.
Don't waste your energy, Walker.
You closed it you can open it!
[BAK]
I refuse.
[LI KEI]
Walker, calm down!
[ALLEN] So you're fine
just letting Fo die?
[BAK] You don't get it.
Exorcists are the only hope
we have against the Akuma.
If you die, that's one
less in this world,
and that means we are that much
closer to losing this war.
Forget about Fo.
You don't mean that.
[BAK] If you really cared
about her, Allen,
you'll endure her loss...
and continue moving forward.
[ALLEN] Drop the stoic
leader act, Bak.
The truth is you're on the verge
of losing control yourself.
You've broken out
in hives again.
[BAK]
Uh?
[ALLEN]
And you're crying.
Uh! What?
I don't know what you mean!
[ALLEN] You can't hide it.
You feel the same way as me.
I'll open this myself.
[ALL]
What?
[ALLEN] You tell me to move
forward, then block my way?
No.
I'll break through this
wall and keeping going!
You don't have any
objection, do you?
It's my choice to make!
Do I object?
Of course I do!
Grab this idiot!
[LI KEI]
Right away, Chief!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[WONG]
Please excuse us.
[ALLEN]
Ow!
Why are you doing this?
Admit it!
You don't want Fo to die so
let me go and rescue her!
You don't have to say anything!
Your face speaks volumes!
Leave my hives outta this!
In case you forgot, that
Akuma's dark matter attack
left your body decomposed
almost down to molecules!
You don't stand a chance!
The slightest bump could
tear your body apart!
Only an idiot would let you
go into battle right now!
And you'd be stupid to want
to fight in your condition!
So shut up and follow
my orders, Exorcist!
[ALLEN] You can't tell me
what to do, Director Bak.
[BAK]
Why not?
[ALLEN]
I'll reveal to HQ
you've secretly been taking
pictures of Lenalee.
[BAK groans]
What?!
No telling what Komui
might do to you.
My guess is,
after he's through, you'll wish
that Level Three got you first.
[BAK]
You're a monster!
[LENALEE]
I can't believe this.
I trusted you, Bak!
And you've been spying
on me like a pervert!
You're disgusting!
Forgive me! Please!
[BAK screams]
[BAK whimpering]
Is that true?
I had no idea.
[ALLEN grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALLEN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
I didn't think you'd
resort to blackmail.
But it doesn't matter.
I won't let you pass.
There are some things
you can't change!
I won't let you through.
We're talking about
a Level Three Akuma.
Look at you! You
won't last a minute.
Fo went in there
to buy us all time
and we're wasting it
arguing like this!
You're wasting time!
I'm not backing down!
And you're not going
to change my mind!
When we met, one of the
first things you asked me
was if I wanted to return to
the battlefield! Remember?
I said yes and that
hasn't changed!
The only way you're gonna get
that wish is if you become
an Exorcist again!
But guess what?!
You're not! You're an
ordinary human being
until your Innocence
gets revived! Got it?
You're wrong!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ALLEN whimpers]
You're wrong. I'm not...
I'm not... a human being.
That Akuma... When
I saw him earlier...
...I felt the blood begin
to stir inside of me.
Like it was unfrozen.
I heard my heart pounding as if
it hadn't been beating
until that moment.
Like I had been brought
back from the dead.
And those feelings
circulating through my body
made it feel good
to be alive again.
What are you...
What're you trying to say?
[ALLEN]
I know the truth.
[gasps]
[FO grunting]
[AKUMA A roars]
[ALLEN]
You made an observation earlier.
My entire existence is like
one Anti-Akuma weapon.
[FO groaning]
[AKUMA A chuckles]
[ALLEN]
It wasn't just a metaphor.
[screaming]
[AKUMA A chuckles]
What my heart
wanted all this time,
the most important thing
to me, was killing Akuma!
I'm not a human anymore!
I am an Exorcist, Bak!
And I have to return
to the battlefield!
[ALLEN]
Let me fight Akuma!
[ALL gasp]
Wong! Li Kei!
We're okay, I think.
He's gone.
What could have happened to him?
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
I'm going.
Thank you for everything, Bak.
You can't.
[BAK]
Houshin.
His arm and eye aren't weapons.
His very existence is.
[BAK]
Only 15 years old,
and cursed by the Akuma.
[ALLEN]
Thank you all very much.
For everything you've
done to help me.
I'm truly grateful.
With all my heart.
I'm not a human anymore!
I only said that to try
and protect you, Allen.
Not hurt you.
[BAK]
I'm sorry.
[AKUMA A] I expected more
of a fight out of you.
I don't understand why the Noah
wanted a weakling
so desperately.
Even going so far
as to use the Ark.
Tell me, Allen Walker,
before you die--
who are you?
I'm a kid. Nothing more.
[AKUMA A]
Correction.
You are nothing.
[FO screams]
[AKUMA A laughs]
Walker.
What did you do? Who are you?
I'm an Exorcist.
[ALLEN] In order to
buy us time and escape,
Fo challenged a Level Three
Akuma by herself.
But I refuse to
leave her to die.
One direct hit, and I'm dead.
If I'm going to save her
and win this fight,
I need to try
something desperate.
On the next D.Gray-man :
"God's Clown!"
Your name's Short Stack.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
So what am I supposed
to call him?
Actually, I don't think
he even has a name.
I figured.
[AKUMA A]
What?! I don't have a name?!