Two hundred ninety...
seven...
Two hundred ninety-eight...
Two hundred ninety-nine...
Three hundred.
What a beautiful morning.
Kanda...
What was that sound just now?
I don't know...
Wait a minute, why am
I even talking to you...?
Get lost.
But what if someone
was in an accident?
Oh please...
As if you would
even do anything.
I bet his assignment
didn't go as he had wanted.
That's probably why Kanda's
being so grumpy this morning.
I guess so...
Lenalee, did you happen to
hear that loud crash just now?
It was most likely
the Science Division
working on an experiment...
I'm sorry about
my brother and his team.
They can be noisy sometimes.
Oh, don't worry about it...
Well...
My next stop is
to the dining hall.
You can't go there!
Not just yet!
It's just that everybody
is in the middle of
cleaning down there.
Plus we shouldn't
bother Jerry right now.
Oh, well, I'll go down
there and give him a hand.
No!
I'm pretty sure they
have plenty of hands...
Why don't you help me
deliver some coffee
to my brother and
the other scientists?
What do you say?
No problem, I can do that.
Section Leader Reever,
why do I get the feeling
this project will never
end in our lifetime?
Don't give up, Johnny.
It'll end soon
enough... hopefully.
That reminds me.
We need to get
to a good stopping point
by the end of the day.
Don't forget.
We're throwing a welcoming
party for Allen later.
Hey, Number Sixty-Five...
Up for lending your
MC talents to the party?
I could keep that
party going all night
if any of you could handle it.
Oh, man, you have no
idea how much money
I'd pay for a skill like that.
Geez, what's the
Chief doing in there?
Doesn't he know how much
work we have on our plates...?
The least he could do is come
help us out for awhile.
Take it easy, Johnny...
Who knows, he might be
inventing something brilliant.
Come on!
Hey, everyone...!
How'd you like to meet the
Savior of the Science Division?
Huh?
I think he's gone mad.
Komui what is the point of
that ridiculously large robot?
Wait, is that thing
wearing a hat?
Allow me to introduce
to you the state-of-the-art
advanced productivity robot...
And the best part...?
We won't have to work
as much from now on!
Are you sure?
Of course I am!
As long as this robot's around,
our workload will
be reduced by...
Fifty percent!
Fantastic!
Maybe now we can get some sleep!
Wow, you called it, sir...
Chief Komui really was
inventing something brilliant.
How did you know that?
I...
We're so lucky to have you, sir!
Yes, yes...
I'm a master of science...
Now why don't you all shower
me with groveling praise?
As the night exists
to await the dawn...
golden rays of hope are
shining down upon us
with dreams of relaxation!
It's about time we got some
well-earned vacation...
I'll finally be able
to visit my son!
Chief, we should
boot it up right now
and see how it works!
We'll do that as soon as we
come up with a name for it.
Huh? You want to
give it a name?
Let's see, what would
be a good one...?
If anyone has any
suggestions then speak up.
I don't know...
How about Mister
beep-boop-beep-boop?
Uhh, no.
Innocender Z!
Eww... no!
Why don't you go ahead
and pick the name, Chief.
Okay...
How about...
Sir Komlin the Second!
I guess that works
but why is it the second?
Well...
because the first one
lived a very short life...
It met its end when Kanda
decided to slice it into pieces.
He claimed that it ate his
soba noodles or something.
Or he pitied it and
put it out of its misery.
Yeah or maybe Kanda
was just in one
of his famous grumpy moods.
Either way Chief,
we think Sir Komlin the
Second is a fantastic name...
Right?
Sure do!
Great...!
Then it's decided.
Sir Komlin the Second...!
I'm counting on you son!
Komui.
Time for a break.
Lenalee, hello.
Who wants some coffee?
I'd love some.
Why are you here?
Oh, I...
I had asked him to
help me carry the coffee.
Well...
Help yourself everybody.
Wow, I had no idea
robots could drink coffee.
How funny.
You still have a
lot to learn Allen.
He may be my alter-ego,
but he is still only a robot.
Everyone knows robots are
incapable of drinking fluids.
Oh no, he drank it.
That can't be very good.
I am Sir Komlin the Second,
and it is my duty to aid in
strengthening Exorcists.
That's it boy, that's it.
You're doing really well.
Keep it up.
Chief, does your robot
have an off switch,
because I think
something's wrong with it!
What the hell are you doing
talking like that
in front of him!
You're going to give him a
complex, he's just a baby!
A perfect, innocent baby!
Take it easy, Brother.
I must operate on this
woman to make her more manly.
Huh?
Why would anyone want
to make Lenalee more manly?
No, Sir Komlin the Second!
You can't do it!
You can't!
But she needs strengthening,
and the only way to do
so is by butching her up.
She wants it.
She needs it!
Run, Lenalee, run!
Get out of here!
She must not escape
before the operation!
Lenalee!
Oh no!
What should we do?!
I'm getting excited
and I don't even know why!
Why would you even
say something like that?!
Quick...!
Somebody stop him!
I think he's gonna
eat my sister!
Geez, why don't
you panic already...?
Now where did I put
that stupid thing.
Chief...!
You're gonna have to show me
where that main circuit is!
Huh...?
Oh, that's right...
What...? NOOO!
You can't destroy my baby!
Not after the hours upon hours
of blood, sweat, and tears
I put him into making him!
So put down that gun,
you murderer!
Okay...
So you don't care?
Forget about Lenalee?
AHHHH!
Now I don't know what to do!!!
Just make up your mind.
Brother...!
Get me down from here!
OHHHH!
I'm trying my best,
my sweet sister!
I... love my sister...
But I also love
Sir Komlin the Second...
What a moral quandary!
Of course...
I completely forgot,
that Allen is with us today.
Sir Komlin...!
I've got great news...
It turns out that our
newest Exorcist Allen Walker
is having trouble with his
Anti-Akuma Weapon.
What?
Do you think you
could fix it for him?
An injury.
Huh?
Dammit Chief!
Looks like the Chief's
throwing Allen to the wolves.
He's evil.
Priority has changed.
Allen Walker's injury
takes precedence
over manliness
increase operation.
How... dare you.
He gassed her!
He gassed Lenalee!
She'll be okay, guys.
I have a great view from here.
Thanks a lot, 65.
Now I must capture Allen Walker.
Expecting resistence...
Lock on.
Allen!
Just run!
But where should I go?!
It doesn't matter...!
Get outta the way kid!
Oh... Right!
Pursue the target at all costs.
He must be caught.
It is for his own good.
Aww, man...
Lenalee... Lenalee...!
Lenalee, snap out of it!
Come on, sis.
Why won't she
answer me?! Why??!!!
It's not looking good for Allen.
That's a safe assessment.
I wouldn't worry.
His battery doesn't
have a full charge
so he should be
out of juice soon.
Unless he used those
extended batteries
we've been working on.
Even though Allen has the
powers of an Exorcist,
he's still only
flesh and blood.
Poor guy's probably on
an empty stomach, too.
Listen up, everyone.
We need to stop this nonsense
before it gets
anymore out of hand...
The Order doesn't
like to pay overtime
but they also wouldn't hesitate
to cut all of our salaries.
Ouch.
Now that's evil.
If you don't want
that to happen then
we need to stop that thing
immediately and save Allen...
Are you ready?
Yes, sir!
Russell's on recon...
Number Sixty-Five,
you're Allen's guide...
The rest of you,
wait for instructions.
Roger that, sir!
Section Leader Reever,
I have a really good idea for a
rescue plan that we could use.
Yeah...?
Let's hear it.
I like to call it the
"Tears of Sadness
become a Waterfall of Hope"
hostage rescue mission.
I meant the details of the plan.
We'll just catch
him with this rope.
Rope catching...?
Please sir, just try
to have an open mind...
Sometimes in science we have to
resort to primitive techniques.
Well I guess it's worth a shot.
Here goes!
That didn't work at all!!!
That was a world
record at failure.
The target is moving west
in the northeast quadrant
at thirty kilometers an hour.
Yeah...
This is the perfect
opportunity to launch my plan.
Let's hear it Johnny.
I just hope it's
better than Tap's.
And...
POW!
Another robot?!
I don't understand
why it's holding a broom.
It looks like one of
those cleaner thingy's
that you use to
vacuum the floor with.
Johnny...
There better be a good
explanation for this.
Actually it's something
I've been cooking up
in my head for years for
just a situation like this.
It's a new bot for the lab!
It not only sweeps,
but it also holds
the potential ability
to slay even the
most powerful Akuma!
It's the ultimate weapon!
Go... get 'em!
No, no, no.
You've got to be kidding me!
Not another robot...!
Wait a minute.
Is that a vacuum cleaner
attached to it?
Allen!
Get to the storage room!
Where's that?
It's this way Allen!
Just follow me!
Okay I'm coming!
Hurry!
Are you sure that
thing can handle itself?
Okay...
I made it inside the
storage room, Johnny.
Good job, Allen.
Now you just
leave the rest to me.
Thank, God.
Ah great!
It's cleaning the floor now!
You're kidding me...!
It's programmed so well, it
won't ignore the tiniest bit
of dust--even
in times of crisis!
It didn't work.
Why am I not surprised...?
This is Reever.
Are you guys ready?
Yes we are, sir!
Stand by...
Allen, you'll have to head
over to the main hall,
we'll try to mount
a rescue from there.
Stop running.
I am only trying to
treat your injuries.
Then tell me why you're trying
to kill me with those missiles?!
Don't panic Allen...
C'mon...
This way.
Thanks!
Okay, I'm here!
Where are you guys?
Allen, you made it!
Oh, hey everyone.
Sorry about the wait.
We'll get you to
safety this time.
It's almost here.
Johnny... Do it!
Yes, sir, right away!
Energy replenishment complete!
Distance two-hundred.
Firing angle is set.
Never underestimate a geek...!
Cause we know how
to bring the pain!
Yeah!
Don't shoot Sir Komlin!!!
Don't shoot my baby!
He's all I have!!!
Chief, let go! I can't breathe!
Don't you care at all
what happens to Allen?!
Don't blame my
baby for everything!!!
CHIEF!!!
Ahh!! The Chief is a traitor!!
What do you guys
expect me to do?!
What's all the fuss about?
Kanda...?! I'll
explain it later...
But we need to stop this robot.
It would be a lot easier if
we knew what its weakness was.
Only an amateur wouldn't be
able to see its weak spot.
Huh?
I had the joy of destroying
a very similar robot
to this in the past.
So where's its weak point?
Just tell me!
Hit it in the scruff, kid.
In its scruff...
Got it...
Wait...!
What the heck's scruff?
Well that's a shame isn't it...?
I guess it's your
fate to die, huh?
No...!
You think you're funny,
don't ya, Kanda?!
It's sneaking up
from behind you...!
Allen!
Watch your back!
Crap!
Allen Walker
has been captured...
Proceed to operating
room immediately.
Allen!
Shaving, carving, gashing, cuts.
We just want to spill some guts!
I have no other choice...
Innocence...
Activate!
Oh wow!
Is that the new
Anti-Akuma Weapon?!
What the hell was that for?!!
My body feels
like butterflies...
He shot a blowgun at Allen!
But if he uses his weapon
on Sir Komlin the
Second he'll hurt him...!
I can't move...
I think I'm paralyzed.
No!
Fight it boy!
Innocence...
Activate.
What about Allen?
Can you see him?
Allen.
You okay?
Yeah...
Never been better.
Take my hand.
I'm glad you're alright...
I thought we had lost
our newest member
to Komui's latest
scientific debacle...
That was a close one.
All this over a useless robot.
Sir Komlin the Second sucks!
We should melt it down!
Melt it down! Melt it down!
It's not Sir Komlin's fault...!
It's all because of the coffee!
You should condemn the
coffee, not the offender...!
Have some compassion...
He's just a little boy.
Brother.
Lenalee! You've got to
stop these monsters!
Go to your room and think
about what you've done.
I'm really sorry
about all this, Allen.
It's fine.
The Chief's really a good man...
He had great intentions
by building that robot
to treat Exorcists,
but it always seems
to get out of hand.
Or is a complete failure.
Right about that...
I'm just relieved that
no one was seriously hurt.
Now that that's over,
would you mind
joining me again, Allen?
It's for you.
Me?
You really thought
we'd let you join us
without a welcoming party?
Everyone was up
all night gettin ready!
That's why I was
acting weird today.
I didn't want to
spoil the surprise...
Here...
Your very own coffee mug.
Welcome to the family Allen...
You're with us now...
Cheers.
We're so glad to have you Allen.
Welcome back... son.
It's good to be back.
I can't stand plain food.
You stupid pile of junk...!
I told you to make it sweet!
Please Skin, have some courtesy.
Can't the beatings
wait until after our meal?
I'm leaving...
I refuse to eat that drivel.
Have it your way...
You can't even
pretend to like it...
how uncultured.
Take it easy, Tyki...
Let's keep things civil.
We're trying to have
a nice family dinner.
Isn't that right...
Lord Millennium...?
So I was thinking maybe
you could set the mood
for the rest of the evening
by telling us exactly
why we're here.
Unless I'm mistaken...
it's time for us
to start the party...
There exists a village
where the same day
is repeated over
and over again...
It is in this place where
I encounter the woman Miranda.
On the next episode
of D. Gray-man:
"The Rewinding Town."
Bring forth salvation to this
tormented Akuma's soul.