[THUG 06A] Hey, Kobayashi!
Get your ass back here!
[yelling]
[CAT 6A yowls]
[THUG 06B]
I'm gonna kill you!
[KOBAYASHI panting]
Ah!
[KIDS laughing]
[panting]
[gasps]
Oh! He's not dead.
Morning!
Why ya sleepin' in the trash?
Where's your clothes?
[KOBAYASHI groans]
I have no idea.
I might have drunk
too much last night.
[KIDS chuckling]
[KOBAYASHI sighs]
Upsy‐daisy.
What are you kids doing
wandering around at this hour?
The morning commute
is when we do
some of our best work!
Heh! Looks like your
business is booming.
And you're only aiming for
the bougie types, right?
‐‐Yeah, duh.
‐‐'Cause they've got money.
Huh? Who's that clown?
Hey, what's up?
[SUGIMOTO]
Shu!
[RENKO giggles]
What is he doing?
[YOSHIO chuckles]
It looks fun. Let's go find out.
[SUGIMOTO]
Shu! Shu‐shu!
[SABURO] Hey, mister.
What are you doing?
Shu! Cuttin' the sun.
That's right.
Shu! 'Cause I wanna shine
brighter than that light.
Shu! Shu! Shu!
‐‐[KIDS laugh]
‐‐[SUGIMOTO] Shu‐shu! Shu!
Sugimoto.
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh...?
Kitty...?
Didn't know you
were back in town.
Diamond head!
[KOBAYASHI groans]
♪ Done with doing my time ♪
♪ Roll down to my hometown
just to bust a fly rhyme ♪
♪ Nothing compares to
the air on the outside ♪
♪ And buying any kind
of food that I wanna try ♪
[KIDS, KOBAYASHI]
Uhh...
[SUGIMOTO]
So, Kitty.
Whatcha been up
to while I was in?
Hah. Well, these kids
are all students from
the cram school where
I've been teaching‐‐
‐‐[groans]
‐‐I'll bury you.
I'm a... detective.
Heh! Detective Kitty now, huh?
[POTTER]
Hey, Boss!
[panting]
I scored a big one.
Kabukinger Z!
[SUGIMOTO]
Hoo, yeah! Feel the power!
Yeah! Now smash
that post button!
Yeet!
Vile demons begone!
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[SUGIMOTO]
Has it sold?
[POTTER]
It's still posting.
[SUGIMOTO]
How 'bout now?
You were talking to that
freakshow like you know him.
[SUGIMOTO]
Make it go faster!
He's Sugimoto
from the Kaneko family.
So is "Kitty" like your
street name or what?
Wait, so why "Kitty?"
Doesn't "Tora" mean tiger?
Yeah, it does.
[KOBAYASHI]
This is Shinjuku's West Side.
A tidy grid of well‐lit streets,
teeming with smiling citizens,
walled off from the morass
of crime and chaos
swirling just to the east.
There, on the dark
streets of Kabukicho,
where the trumpeting of
elephants rings in the hour
and villains lurk in every
shadow, six detectives roam.
Freaks, geeks, losers,
and loons to a one.
Where they roam,
chaos will surely follow.
And the battle's about to
start heating up again today,
so come check it out!
[YOSHIO] All right,
I finished updating your list
of local criminals.
You work fast.
[YOSHIO] Hey. When are you
gonna give me a bigger job?
[SHERLOCK]
Pfft. Come back in ten years.
[YOSHIO growls]
[YUYA]
Dreams for the future?
How lame is that?
Well, if we're talking
about our futures,
maybe we should
ask the grown‐ups.
[SABURO]
Hah! Yeah, good idea!
[YUYA]
Hey. Go‐Go.
Was it your dream
to be a detective?
[FUYUTO]
Hmph! No.
My dream has always been to get
rich and move to the West‐‐
[KIDS]
Never gonna happen!
That's a silly
dream for a virgin.
[grunts] What's that
have to do with anything?!
Putting aside whether
it's true or not...
What is a virgin?
I heard somewhere
it's a word for a person
who's never fired a rocket
beam out of their body.
[SABURO]
Then I'm a virgin, too!
[YUYA]
Yeah, me, three!
What about you?
Why did you become a detective?
So you could do rakugo, right?
[WATSON grunts]
‐‐So you could do rakugo?
‐‐What's that mean?
I don't get it.
[overlapping talking]
So, uh, how 'bout you guys?
What are your dreams?
Detective!
None. If I can't eat 'em,
I don't need 'em!
Marry someone who makes
a hundred million a year.
I wanna live off
my real estate portfolio.
[LYCHEE] Hmm... I wanna
fire the rocket beam.
[WATSON sighs]
My dream...
I wanna be the leader
who protects this town!
[KIDS]
Never gonna happen!
[RENKO] We've already
got the Captain for that!
[YUYA] Yeah, the Captain might
be able to run this place.
[SABURO]
But definitely not Yoshio.
[YUYA]
What about you, Kitty?
[KOBAYASHI]
Huh?
Who's Kitty?
This guy. We used to
call him Kobayashi,
but turns out that
was a just a nickname.
That's backwards!
Wait, that's not the problem.
We heard some random guy
from the Kaneko gang
calling him "Kitty."
[MORIARTY]
Huh? Hey, that's right.
Didn't you used to work
for the Kaneko family
before you became a detective?
[GROUP gasping]
I'd never heard about that!
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[YOSHIO]
Why did you quit?
'Cause being a detective
is a way better gig for sure!
That's a lie!
[KOBAYASHI]
Tch! I got tossed out.
‐‐Hah!
‐‐That's the lamest reason ever.
Yeah, ya big loser.
Guys. I say we've
done enough homework.
Let's go back
to the secret base!
For sure!
You wanna come?
[MORIARTY]
Mm... I'm good, thanks.
‐‐[JURI groans]
‐‐[YUYA] Again?
You know, I used to have
a secret base, too!
So where is it?
I promise I won't tell, guys!
[YUYA] Why would we want
someone who got kicked out
of another gang?
Heh. Fair enough.
Here you go! Lunch Special: X.
That's not food...
[SUGIMOTO]
Shu! Shu‐shu! Shu!
Why'd you stop?
[YUYA]
It's that guy from before.
‐‐Shu! Shu! Shu‐shu!
‐‐I'm sorry...
Don't be.
Just bring me that paper.
‐‐Mwah!
‐‐[SHOPKEEP 06A] Ugh!
All the paper, you get me?
Yes.
Woo‐hoo‐hoo! That's sweet!
[SABURO] Is that... a whole
stack of Dokkiri‐man?
How? I haven't been able to
find that stuff anywhere!
[YOSHIO] Holy crap,
look at all that chocolate!
Good talkin' with you, bruh.
See ya next month.
[KIDS gasp]
[KIDS]
Huh...
He almost had us.
[YOSHIO]
Yeah...
[SHOPKEEP 06A groans]
[YUYA] Ugh. This neighborhood's
really goin' downhill.
Yeah, right?
I think the Irregulars need to
take matters into our own hands.
Ah... There's something
I need to do.
I'll catch up later!
‐‐Okay?
‐‐Gotta poop?
If that guy sold
that sticker online,
he could get a lot of money
for it, couldn't he?
Yeah. Foils go for
at least a hundred thou.
Real rare ones get up
to a million or more.
Dang!
Bet that guy's
selling them himself.
‐‐Scumbag.
‐‐What a creep.
[SUGIMOTO grunting]
[YOSHIO]
'Scuse me, sir.
Shu.
[YOSHIO panting]
[chuckles]
[SUGIMOTO] Looks like
the old man's gone soft
while I was stuck in the pen.
Screw that crap!
Now that I'm out,
I gotta start getting paid
so I can go my own way.
Then I blow up, roll back into
Kaneko's turf, get my war on!
[POTTER]
Hey, Bro! That Kabukinger Z.
It just sold and
I made 20,000 yen!
[SUGIMOTO chuckles]
That's lunch money next to
what I'm about to bring, dude.
Because I got that
high‐end product, son.
The hottest sticker
on the market is right‐‐
Huh...?
‐‐[door bells jingle]
‐‐Come on in!
[POTTER]
This is the place, bro!
[SUGIMOTO groaning]
Huh...?
[growls]
[SUGIMOTO]
Kitty! Cross counter!
Ahh!
♪ Sugimoto in the place ♪
♪ Nata de coco,
wanna stick it in my face ♪
♪ I go like Nomo,
let nobody take a base ♪
♪ A lot of body hair
suits my taste! ♪
[POTTER growls] No, bro.
He already knows who you are!
‐‐[SUGIMOTO growls]
‐‐Hold up. I got this.
♪ Yo, check it, son. ♪
♪ My bro had himself
an envelope, yo, ♪
♪ but some kid stole it
and that's not dope! ♪
♪ And he was one of those kids
who we saw with you before! ♪
♪ So, yo! Where'd he go?! ♪
♪ Yo, yo! ♪
Word.
[KOBAYASHI SIGHS]
How would I know?
‐‐[phone rings]
‐‐[KOBAYASHI grunts]
That the boy?
‐‐Nah, bro.
‐‐Grab him.
‐‐Okay!
‐‐[KOBAYASHI groans]
Get the hell offa me,
you stupid meathead!
[grunts]
[SABURO]
Oh. Hey, Kitty.
Do you think you could steal us
some food from the bar?
Heh. Hey there!
Kobayashi's off
takin' a wicked dump.
But I'm a friend of his,
so you can tell me whatever
you woulda told him.
Lemme know where you
want him to bring the food
and I'll pass it on.
[SABURO] The sixth floor
of the old Kabuki Bowl.
Right, got it. Thanks, mister!
Kobayashi's coming?
Is he gonna bring us food?
Yep.
Some friend of his
picked up the phone.
He said Kitty was takin' a dump,
but that he would pass it on.
[YOSHIO]
Hmm...
[elephant trumpets]
[KOBAYASHI grunting, groaning]]
‐‐[gasping]
‐‐Mister Kobayashi!
What happened to you?
The kids are in danger, guys.
One of Kaneko's thugs is
making his way to their base.
That sounds fun!
The guy used to be my boss.
He just got out of the joint.
Sugimoto, huh?
He never stays
out of jail very long.
Biggest slimeball
in the whole family.
What would a guy
like that want with the kids?
He said they pickpocketed him.
Rat bastard.
He took my phone from me
and tricked them into
telling him where
their base is. Dammit!
‐‐[WATSON] Wait!
‐‐Ah! [groans]
Get it together, buddy.
He might know where their
base is, but you still don't.
[KOBAYASHI growls]
I know!
Wait, how are we ever gonna find
the place if it's a secret?
Stop, Kuma, it's way too early
to be sounding that discouraged.
Ooh! You say that like you've
got some kinda plan, old man.
My plan is to text
Kobayashi. That's it.
‐‐Huh?!
‐‐[KOBAYASHI gasps]
[RENKO] Let go of me,
you fat sack of crap!
What are you doing?!
Put me down right now unless
you wanna find out how far
I can put my fist
down your throat!
You creepy,
giant‐baby‐looking piece of‐‐
[grunts]
Nothing, bro. None of them
have the envelope.
You kids know
the name "Moriarty"?
‐‐Well?
‐‐[gasping]
Yeah, Moriarty's our captain!
Says he's gonna be showing up
with the cash any minute now.
[overlapping yelling]
[RENKO] What are you
doing with Kitty's phone?!
[SUGIMOTO chuckles] You kids
like that nickname, too, huh?
Long as we're here,
how 'bout I tell you
why we call him "Kitty."
That damn coward.
He turned his back
on the Kaneko gang.
[SUGIMOTO]
Where's our money at, Wakazo?
Ah! He's not there.
He must have known somehow!
[grunts]
You try'na tell me
your dumb ass couldn't even
collect from that
weedy little tool?
[KOBAYASHI]
I... I'm sorry.
Feh! Yeah? You sure
you didn't let him go?
What? No way!
‐‐I have no‐‐
‐‐Look me in the eye,
you worthless little shit!
[KOBAYASHI groans]
[SUGIMOTO growls]
[THUG 06A] Hey, Kobayashi!
Get your ass back here!
[overlapping yelling]
[CAT 6A yowls]
[THUG 06B]
I'm gonna kill you!
[SUGIMOTO]
Sugi‐nado warning!
[yells]
[SUGIMOTO]
♪ Call yourself a tiger ♪
♪ 'cause you think
you're ballin' ♪
♪ You're just a
shitty little kitty ♪
♪ who's in for a maulin' ♪
♪ Pull a stunt like that,
think you'll get a pass? ♪
♪ Think again, little man,
snake in the grass ♪
♪ The only thing you'll get
is a look at my ass ♪
Get dunked on!
[banging]
That must be our boy.
Yeah.
‐‐[KIDS gasping]
‐‐[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI panting]
[growls]
[RENKO]
What are you doing?!
Put me down right now unless
you wanna find out how far
I can put my fist
down your throat!
[SUGIMOTO]
"Moriarty"...?
[RENKO grunting]
‐‐[cell notification dings]
‐‐[MORIARTY] Ah! Got an answer!
Let's see...
Says they're on the sixth floor
of the Kabuki Bowl building.
[KOBAYASHI snarls]
[WATSON]
Wait, Kobayashi!
That idiot's never gonna learn.
[WATSON whimpers]
[KOBAYASHI growls]
Hey! You gotta pay for those!
[SHERLOCK] It's the same reason
he got kicked out of the gang.
[SUGIMOTO] Kitty! What the hell
are you doing here?!
[KOBAYASHI growls]
[SUGIMOTO groans]
‐‐[KOBAYASHI whooping]
‐‐[POTTER grunts]
Run! Get out of here!
‐‐[YOSHIO] Kobayashi!
‐‐[JURI] Nice work!
[SHERLOCK] The guy's got a heart
of gold and a brain of mush.
[KOBAYASHI rasps]
[KOBAYASHI] If you can't pay,
then you shouldn't have
taken out the loan, dickweed.
‐‐Tch.
‐‐[WAKAZO sobbing]
Is there anything
worth anything in here?
Hmm?
What the hell?
Heh! All the time you
spent drawing this crap,
you coulda been out there
‐‐getting a job to pay your‐‐
‐‐Don't touch that!
[KOBAYASHI laughs]
Man, what a great manga!
Hey, thank you.
You were gonna
beat me up, right?
Still wouldn't get me
the money, now would it?
[WAKAZO] But you know what
will happen if you do this!
[KOBAYASHI]
Run. Quit wasting time.
There's no reason
for you to go this far.
[KOBAYASHI] Tch.
Of course I got a reason.
I never met anyone like you.
For everyone I've known
since I was a kid,
growing up meant giving up.
I figured that's
how real life was.
I guess there's
still a part of me
that wants better.
I think guys like you deserve
to chase your dreams.
‐‐[WAKAZO grunts]
‐‐[car tires screech]
[KOBAYASHI]
That's them. You gotta go.
Tora, thanks so much.
[SUGIMOTO]
Yo, Wakazo. Pay up!
You can't run forever!
[KOBAYASHI sighs]
I'll pay! I'll get you
your money back!
[KOBAYASHI rasping]
[gasps]
[POTTER screams]
‐‐[sobbing]
‐‐[coughs]
‐‐[JURI] Kobayashi!
‐‐[YOSHIO] You okay?
Ah! Why are you
still here?! Get away!
‐‐[YUYA] Let's go!
‐‐[JURI] Yeah!
Ha...!
‐‐[glass shatters]
‐‐[KOBAYASHI] Agh!
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐What're you stopping for?!
We're not waiting for you!
[YOSHIO growls]
[KOBAYASHI groaning]
[SUGIMOTO] It's about time
we get you fixed, Kitty!
Say bye‐bye to your balls!
[YOSHIO]
I'm the one who took your money!
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh...?
Here. You can have it back,
so please just let him go!
No... The kid was working for
me‐‐
‐‐Ah!
‐‐[YOSHIO gasps] Bastard!
[SUGIMOTO]
I don't see what difference
that even makes anymore.
Run... Get away...
[gasps, whimpers]
[POTTER chuckles]
Hey, bro, I think I got the kid!
[SUGIMOTO grunts]
Good work, Potter.
Hold his right arm out straight.
[POTTER]
Huh?
The boy here needs to learn.
This is what we do
to thieves in this town.
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[POTTER]
Right, Boss!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[KOBAYASHI]
Leave him... alone...
[SUGIMOTO]
Huh...?
♪ Kitty with his one nut
stupid looking hair cut ♪
♪ Never saving anyone,
traded in his brains for guts ♪
♪ Lift your fists into the sky,
cry if ya want ♪
♪ A tabby try'na live
a tiger life, though? ♪
What!
[KOBAYASHI growls softl]
[KOBAYASHI grunting]
[KANEKO]
This is it? The full balance.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yes, Boss.
Huh?
Ah?
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI whimpers]
[KOBAYASHI sobbing]
[KOBAYASHI]
My name... isn't Kitty...
Uh... My name...
[YOSHIO whimpers]
[SUGIMOTO chuckles]
...is Torataro!
[screams
[SUGIMOTO groans]
No, Bro!
[SUGIMOTO growls]
[snarls]
[gasps]
Boss!
[WATSON]
Everyone... You okay?
Sugimoto, it's time to atone.
I was only trying to
get your money back!
[KANEKO] And would this
be the Dokkiri‐man sticker
that I heard about?
You're not talking
your way out of this, Sugimoto.
[SUGIMOTO panting]
[screeches]
[cackles]
Bro!
I... can... fly!
Shu! Shu! Shu!
Shu! Shu‐shu!
Shu!
Shuuu...!
[KOBAYASHI sighs]
I'm really sorry, guys.
You're fine.
[KANEKO]
Kobayashi!
[KOBAYASHI]
Boss!
You're still the same
moron you always were.
[KOBAYASHI]
Sorry for the trouble.
[KANEKO]
Stick to your guns, kid.
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
Thanks.
Right. Let's go.
[KOBAYASHI sighs]
‐‐[KOBAYASHI groans]
‐‐[KIDS gasping]
[KOBAYASHI chuckles]
[overlapping talking]
[KOBAYASHI]
Don't touch me, it hurts!
Now. Let's give
that guy his money back.
And since it's
a special occasion,
whatever you want's on me!
[KIDS cheer]
[overlapping yelling]
Captain. This was all my fault.
You did mess up,
and your friends
nearly paid the price.
But in the end, you had the
courage to stand up for them.
And that is the leadership
that this town needs.
Ah.
‐‐Hey, Yoshio!
‐‐Captain!
Come on, guys!
[YOSHIO sniffs]
Yeah!
[MORIARTY gasps]
Hey, Captain. What's wrong?
[YOSHIO]
Hmm? Captain?
Aw, crap!
I was supposed to be going
to a concert tonight with
a friend of mine
from school, guys!
Oh, come on!
No worries. See ya, Moriarty!
‐‐Let's go.
‐‐[MORIARTY] Later.
[overlapping talking]
[gasps]
Hey, what are you doing?
[SHERLOCK guffawing]
[MORIARTY]
Huh...?
[MORIARTY chuckles]
You're a goof.
[GODFREY]
Today is the future!
[CROWD]
Future!