Now that Jack's found
out where you live,
it isn't safe for you to
continue staying there anymore.
You need to hide.
Stay off the grid
for a little while.
And I'll go with you.
I'd be happy to serve as
your personal bodyguard.
Nobody would dare lay a hand
on you with me around!
And anyone who tried would
find themselves dead
where they stood!
Hmm?
[screams]
Blood! It's touching me!
[WATSON] Could you please try
to take this seriously, you two?
Stop freaking out, Doctor.
That woman can
take care of herself.
[IRENE sighs]
[HUDSON]
Hmm...
Hmm! Maybe it would be
best if you stayed
with Sherlock for a while.
[WATSON gasps]
Hah! Like hell it would!
I am not allowing that
blue‐eyed demon into my room!
Yes! That sounds wonderful.
[WOMAN moaning]
[SHERLOCK grunts]
[squeals]
And my father was born in Kyoto,
and his family name was Ando...
Oh, dear. You fried
his poor little brain.
Okay. I can't
deny that Sherlock
does brilliant work
as a detective,
but he's not the bodyguard type.
What, didn't you know?
He's also a master
of the art of baritsu.
What is that?
I've never heard of baritsu.
He's a baritsu master?
Shocking. I didn't know.
So is that like a big deal?
[FUYUTO]
It's the biggest deal.
Or so they say, at least.
A real correspondence
combat course
for the cerebral
warrior of today.
Baritsu.
[WATSON]
Uhh...
Well, Doctor. It's time
for you to get packing.
Remember, it's all
for Irene's sake.
You're welcome to stay
here in the bar for a while,
so let's go.
[WATSON] Wait, why am
I getting kicked out?!
[HUDSON]
Oh, come on, darling.
[WATSON]
I like sleeping in a real bed!
"Give back the egg"?
And what egg would that be?
He's talking about
the fried‐egg USB drive.
From that one case?
Yes, Moran's mystery drive.
Jack is coming after me because
he has no way of knowing
that Sherlock has it now.
But I thought
you gave the egg back
to Mycroft in the end.
Not quite.
[SHERLOCK] I gave him
the dummy drive instead.
Whatever's on this drive
should give us a clue...
...to Jack's identity.
[WATSON sighs]
Heh.
This is nice.
The sofa's actually
pretty plush.
[grunts]
[hisses]
[WATSON groans]
[PIPE meowling]
Wha‐‐?! Am I not allowed
to sleep here either?
[hisses]
Fine. Guess I'll
sleep on the floor.
‐‐[PIPE yowls]
‐‐[WATSON screams]
[PIPE grunting]
[WATSON whimpers]
[IRENE] Hmm. I see.
You've already given up
on the password.
I'm not that interested in
what's on the drive.
But you know that Jack is,
and you want to use
it as bait, right?
Hmm? Good guess?
[SHERLOCK sighs]
[knocking]
[WATSON]
Beg your pardon!
Hi, you two.
Could I borrow
the bath for a little bit?
Uh... I'm happy to keep
doing the cleaning,
as long as I can still
use the facilities.
The cleaning
has been dealt with.
[WATSON gasps]
[WATSON]
Wow. I guess it has.
It's never looked this nice.
Or smelled this good.
[IRENE]
Isn't rose a lovely scent?
It's my favorite perfume.
Rose, huh?
As long as you're up here,
would you like me
to make some lunch for you?
[WATSON]
Whoa...
What gives?
I told you that I wanted
canned mangos on mine.
Ah. I'll grab some
out of the pantry.
[IRENE]
You could at least try it first.
[SHERLOCK groans]
[SHERLOCK grunts]
[WATSON gasps]
Here. It'll be even
better with some ponzu.
[SHERLOCK grunts]
[WATSON gasps]
[WATSON sighs]
Hey, old dude! What's up?
We're throwing
water balloons at drunks!
You should come give it
a shot, bet you'll like it!
God's wrath!
[gasps]
[laughter]
Get a job, ya soggy loser!
[gasping]
You brats! Get down here!
Apologize!
You filthy little shits!
[YOSHIO]
My bad, dorks!
[PASSERBY 09B] Get your ass
down here so I can beat it!
[RENKO]
You wanna try next?
It's lots of fun.
Heh. Pass.
There's somewhere that
I really need to be.
Later!
Now what?
I've got nowhere to go.
[FUYUTO]
Don't be scared.
You can do this, Fuyuto!
[FUYUTO]
With this...
With what's in this machine.
I can finally become a real man!
[whimpers]
[WATSON]
Mister Kyogoku?
[FUYUTO (high‐pitched)]
Never heard of 'im.
Okay.
Do you want your money
back from the machine?
[WATSON] Huh? You're asking
somebody out on a date
for the first time?
Yes.
[WATSON]
That's great.
But it might be a little
early to be buying‐‐
No. I won't risk having kids
before I turn 32.
I'm playing it safe.
For the moment, what matters
most is to get to know Maki.
Wha‐‐? Are you
talking about the one
who's always hanging
around here?
Of course.
The one with the bobbed hair
and the red dress.
[WATSON] Wow, I don't
think I'd have guessed
that she was your type.
Ah. My type? Maybe...
I suppose you're right.
She is my type.
You think she's your type, too?
‐‐[FUYUTO] Uh... Probably?
‐‐[MARY chuckles]
[HUDSON giggles]
[WATSON]
By the way...
How much experience do
you have with Maki's type?
Ha! That won't be an issue!
[IRENE]
Hmm. Hey.
There's something
I really wanna do.
But it'll be much more fun
if you do it with me.
[SHERLOCK] Jugemu jugemu goko
no surikire kaijarisuigyo‐no
suigyomats unraimats
furaimats kuunerutokoro...
[MAKI]
Oh, stop!
You're such a funny
guy, Mr. Kyogoku!
[FUYUTO laughs]
Just making conversation.
Ahh...
How I wish that I could
find a sweetheart like you
to be my boyfriend.
Silly, right?
Actually...
I know a special place that
I'd really like to show you.
[MAKI gasps]
Oh, my darling.
I'll be by your side
until the very end!
"And with that,
the two of them set off
into the moonlit"...
What am I even reading?
My plan for our
first date, of course.
You might talk like this,
but when it comes
to Maki, I'm not so sure.
Well, obviously there
are variables to consider.
[FUYUTO] And that is why
I've run enough simulations
to account for every
last one of them!
The battle is won before
the first spear is raised!
You've certainly put
some thought into this.
‐‐[MARY sighs]
‐‐Men are so funny.
‐‐Bless their little hearts.
‐‐[door bell jingles]
[CHINKILL] So? Whatcha
think about this one?
[FUYUTO gulps]
[MAKI]
Mm... He's not quite my type.
‐‐[CHINKILL] Ugh! Good.
‐‐[DIANA] Called it!
‐‐[CHINKILL] I took one look...
‐‐[HUDSON] Hey, girly,
what's going on with you?
[CHINKILL]
So there's this new guy, right?
[FUYUTO]
Ms. Maki Hokari!
Yes?
Um... I was hoping
that I could maybe
have a talk with you
about me and you and us
doing some things together?
[MAKI]
Hmm?
Things like, um, you know.
Just normal adult‐type things.
Like getting martinis together,
and then taking the party back
to the hotel room.
And then you start getting
embarrassed when I go
That's nice.
I'll be going now
if you don't mind.
If you're wondering,
he was hoping to ask you out
on a date.
[FUYUTO] That's right! I wanted
to ask you out on a date!
But you‐‐
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[MARY] FYI, the guy's
got piles of money.
Just thought you'd wanna know.
We can go anywhere you want!
[FUYUTO gasps, laughs]
Yeah! My plan is a success!
Who could have guessed?
[IRENE moaning]
Oh, Sherlock, it's too much!
[panting]
Oh, God! It's so big!
[SHERLOCK whimpering]
What's up, Sherlock?
[SHERLOCK groans]
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[SHERLOCK groans] Tch.
Hello, James.
What are you doing here, lady?
[IRENE] I'm stacking shogi tiles
and hiding from Jack the Ripper.
Well, looks like
I win this round!
Ah. Is that so.
[MAKI] Hmm... I don't know
which one to get.
[FUYUTO whimpers]
This is a problem.
[FUYUTO]
Ah!
I just can't decide.
I think I need them all!
Right! Then that's
what you'll get!
You're that guy from the bar.
Why are you always hanging
out here by the playground?
‐‐No job?
‐‐Are those noodles good?
[WATSON]
Where I choose to go and why
is none of your business.
Don't take my picture!
[YUYA]
I'm adding you to our database
of sketchy middle‐aged dudes
who hang around this area.
Who are you calling sketchy?
I went to med school!
[MORIARTY] And yet, here
you are eating cup noodles
on a park bench,
but there's good news!
I got some tickets
to a rakugo show.
Wanna go? You, me, and Sherlock.
I'm in.
[MORIARTY]
You dummy. What now?
There's only three tickets.
Sorry, but there's no way
we can leave her alone.
Could you please hurry this up?
Oh, don't worry about me.
You boys have fun at your show.
[WATSON sighs]
[MORIARTY] That's that.
Now let's get going.
[WATSON] It's dangerous
to leave you by yourself.
‐‐I can stay here with you.
‐‐[beeping]
Hello? What's up, Yoshio?
Ah? An accident?
[MORIARTY]
I'm coming. Don't go anywhere!
Hey, what's wrong?
It's an emergency!
Go on without me!
I hope everything's okay.
Right. Now then, Doctor.
We are running late!
Uh...
[chuckles]
Do you think it was him?
Jack did this.
Ugh. The kitchen, too?
Did he find the drive?
[sighs]
Clearly, it's not
safe here anymore.
What now? I've got
nowhere left to hide.
[SHERLOCK]
You can use this.
[IRENE]
Hey, can I take this off yet?
[SHERLOCK]
No, you can't.
[IRENE sighs]
We don't know who's
watching us right now.
You need to
disappear for a while.
Keep the mask on.
Will she really
be safe where we're going?
He already found her twice.
Boss Kaneko recommended it,
and he knows how
to keep things hidden.
[SHERLOCK] It's an
old abandoned movie theater
that the Kaneko family
used to operate.
The boss himself hides out here
when there's
a gang war going on.
The three of us are
the only ones who know
that Irene is hiding here.
Let's keep it that way.
Don't tell anybody.
My lips are sealed.
[IRENE] Hmm!
The boss is well prepared.
[SHERLOCK] You'll have
no problem getting by
with what you have on hand here.
[IRENE]
Thank you both.
I've put you two
through a lot of trouble.
That said, could I
ask you to go pick up
a few more things for me?
[SHERLOCK]
Damn that woman.
These things are not needs.
Well...
I don't mind doing the
shopping if you don't want to.
It's fine. I can do it.
Okay. But why?
Wouldn't it make
more sense to split up?
[SHERLOCK]
I've got it.
[WATSON grunts, gasps]
[WATSON]
I'm not useless, you know?
But he treats me like an idiot.
I'm a person
and I have feelings.
Hang on. Are you listening?
Not in the slightest. My bad.
[WATSON]
Is everything all right?
I don't know!
I'm standing at
a crossroads in my life.
‐‐[WATSON] Huh?
‐‐[FUYUTO grunts]
[gasps]
That's some rock.
Tonight is the night
that I confess my love
to my sweet princess.
‐‐[stomach rumbling]
‐‐[groans]
[FUYUTO] And the simulations
are tying my stomach in knots!
Mr. Kyogoku?
This could be bad.
He's in for some surprises.
Good luck, pal.
All that cash wasn't
doing him any good anyway.
Huh?
Come on.
Maki's obviously milking him
for money before she dumps him.
[DIANA]
Damn, girl!
You pawned off every
single thing he gave you?
[CHINKILL]
Ice cold!
[MAKI]
You two. Don't say that so loud.
It was all just way
too expensive for me.
I gotta get myself a pay pig!
[DIANA]
Right? That would be the life!
Really?
You know how seriously
he's taking this, right?
Would you get off
your high horse?
It was never gonna
end well for him.
Yeah, well.
He could blow her away
with his passion.
Keep dreaming.
[FUYUTO gasps]
Ms. Maki Hokari!
[MAKI]
Kyogoku?
[growls]
I'd like to ask you.
[gasps]
Oh, my god!
Did he really?
[gasps]
[FUYUTO]
May I... May I...
May I hold your hand?
[inhales]
I beg you!
A diamond ring
just to hold her hand?
Oh, babe.
That rock's worth
at least a couple handies.
[MAKI gasps]
Thank you. It's lovely.
[gasps]
Finally...
At last, I can hold her hand!
That poor bastard.
This is sad.
But why? Why would you
do all of this for me?
[FUYUTO]
Ah. I want‐‐
Are you after my body?
[gasps] No!
Y‐Y‐You've got me all wrong!
Then what is it?
I...
I‐I want.. to take your
hand in marriage someday.
I'm sorry, but I can't accept.
[gasps]
You can't?
Please... Don't...
It's too soon for that.
We've hardly gotten
to know each other yet.
Let's date like a real couple.
[FUYUTO whimpers]
Maki!
Wait, what?
He did it!
‐‐[CHINKILL whimpers]
‐‐Oh, no...
This is actually kind of sweet!
[CHINKILL]
Good luck, you two!
Congratulations, bud!
[FUYUTO gasps]
Thank you, John.
Remember, if I did it,
then you can, too.
So be bold.
Laugh in the face of failure.
Now then.
Shall we grab ourselves
a drink, darling?
[MAKI]
Let's!
[DIANA, CHINKILL sobbing]
That's it. Now it's time
for me to be bold!
Yeah, good luck!
With whatever you're gonna do.
[WATSON sighs]
[phone rings, buzzes]
[SHERLOCK grunts]
Still all clear.
No movement.
[FUYUTO moaning]
I'm so embarrassed...
I'm just so nervous, Maki.
Oh, be gentle.
[FUYUTO]
O‐Oh, god, Maki!
[WATSON groans]
‐‐[clack]
‐‐[gasps]
[glass bottles clinking]
[metal clanging]
[screams]
Wha... What happened?
[SHERLOCK]
Watson, go check on Irene!
[WATSON gasps]
[SHERLOCK panting]
[KIDS chuckling]
Huh?
‐‐[YUYA gasps] Sherlock?
‐‐Hey! What's wrong?
Operation Tug‐of‐War!
[YUYA, JURI, SABURO]
Roger that!
[VOICE]
Miss Adler. This is the police!
[IRENE]
Hmm?
[VOICE]
Jack got Moriarty!
[gasps]
‐‐[JURI] Pull!
‐‐[SABURO, YUYA] And pull!
[CLOAKED MAN grunts]
[gasps]
[YUYA]
Ah! Hey, it's Daigoro!
Yeah, that's right.
We've got him in
the drifter database.
It says he usually stays
in Kabukicho Park.
Where's our pay?
[IRENE whimpers]
[MYSTERY MAN 7A]
Where is the drive?
[IRENE whimpers]
[MYSTERY MAN 7A growls]
If you're not going to say...
[IRENE gasps]
[WATSON]
Ms. Adler!
[gasps]
[WATSON]
Ms. Adler!
[MORIARTY gasps]
[MORIARTY] It's Jack!
You stay and look after her!
[WATSON] It'll be okay,
just try not to move.
[IRENE whimpers]
Hold on. I'm calling
an ambulance.
[whimpering continues]
[receiver ringing]
You find him?
[MORIARTY]
Mm‐mm.
Hey, Sherlock.
We got Irene to the hospital
and they're treating her now‐‐
She's dead.
L‐‐
[SHERLOCK]
I just got word.
Oh, no...
This is tragic...
[SHERLOCK] The three of us
are the only ones who know
that Irene is hiding here.
Let's keep it that way.
Moriarty...
[WATSON]
What were you doing there?
How did you know?
[IRENE]
Watson.
He's in trouble.
Help Sherlock!