[HUDSON]
This is Shinjuku's West Side.
A tidy grid of
well‐lit streets,
teeming with smiling citizens,
walled off from
the morass of crime and
chaos swirling just to the east.
There, on the dark
streets of Kabukicho,
where the trumpeting of
elephants rings in the hour
and evil lurks in every
shadow, six detectives roam.
Freaks, geeks,
losers and loons to a one.
Where they roam,
chaos will surely follow.
And you, darlings,
are invited to watch
their wild war
of wills and wits.
[WATSON] I'm still
not sure how this works.
Do all the detectives
at the Row House
take on one case
at the same time?
I suppose you would
want to know about all that.
Okay.
When a client brings us a case,
it falls into
one of three ranks.
The lowest is an A‐rank.
For A‐rank jobs,
a client hires one
of the detectives directly.
Basically normal P.I. work.
S‐rank is a step up,
with a minimum reward
of one million yen.
These jobs are open
to all in the row house,
but expenses aren't covered, and
only the one who solves the case
gets to bring home that bacon.
And lastly,
there's the S‐rank with bonus.
Where the client covers all
detective's expenses during
the investigation whether
they solve the case or not.
Naturally, everyone wants
a piece of that action.
Ya follow me, babe?
[HUDSON]
Eyes over here, honey.
Ah! Sorry.
So if I had an A‐rank case and
I wanted to hire Mister Holmes,
how much is that?
Hard to say. He doesn't
care much about money.
He only takes cases
he finds interesting.
[SHERLOCK]
Please get out.
[WOMAN 2A] I only brought
you all of this because
I want to help you get better!
How could you not
want ten days' worth
of vegetable fiber
in a single meal?
I don't need more fiber.
[WOMAN 2A]
I eat two every day
and I've never felt
better in my life.
‐‐Keeps me good 'n regular, too.
‐‐[WATSON] E‐Excuse me.
Mister Holmes,
I want to hire you.
Oh, you're the one
bunking in the storeroom
next door, aren't you?
Yes, the name's John Watson.
Wanna try some?
It's Super Veggieman, and it'll
make your skin soft as satin.
[WATSON]
I was wondering how you did it.
Ah?
A woman in her 30s
would be jealous of your skin.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐And your pulse is so strong.
Oh, you're just too much!
Here. All of these are on me.
[gasps]
Nice to meet you, John.
[WATSON gasps]
Hold on‐‐!
[SHERLOCK]
Make something with that.
"Make something"?
You want me to cook?
I was involved
in a car accident.
My leg is still injured.
[WATSON gasps]
[WATSON groans]
The culprit remains at large.
After being caught on camera
during the gold heist
two weeks ago,
the phantom thief Cobra
has evaded law enforcement.
With the investigation
stalled...
[WATSON]
Food's ready.
What about the can?
Sorry. I couldn't
find anything but oranges.
[grunts]
[SHERLOCK belches]
[WATSON] Um... Would you
agree to take my case
if I paid on completion?
[SHERLOCK] And pick up after me,
do laundry, buy groceries,
clean my room. Oh,
and the bathroom, too.
As you may recall,
I was recently hit by a car.
[meowing]
[BOTH]
Hmm?
I've got a call.
Do you mind?
[sighs]
[MARY]
Hey there!
[MARY giggles]
Hello.
It's nice to meet you,
my name is Mary Morstan.
Are you working for Sherlock?
It's complicated.
Hmm?
[WATSON]
He looks mad!
I'm here! Fabulous
and fashionably late!
Right then. It's time
to introduce our latest client.
[gasps]
Miss Fujiko?
Hi there. Don't
I see you at my shop sometimes?
Yeah. My name is Kobayashi.
Pardon me for interrupting.
But could we begin by discussing
the pay rank for your case?
I have a fair amount
to attend to today.
Ah. Sure.
S‐rank, no bonus.
The reward for solving it
is one million yen.
Hah. A low S.
Best of luck to you,
but I won't be taking part.
[KOBAYASHI growls]
That's the bare
minimum she could pay
to get everybody to show up.
And we'll have to cover
our own expenses, too,
so this isn't really
all that great of a job.
Feh! Well,
screw that guy anyway.
I'll see your case through
to the end, Miss Fujiko!
[FUJIKO sighs]
That's so good to hear.
So, tell us all about it!
Oh. Okay. Thank you.
I'm Fujiko Takamine, and I run
a flower shop on Second Avenue.
I'll start from the beginning.
[FUJIKO] Saori, did you take
care of that bouquet of roses
that Taneyama Farms ordered?
Hey, um, we're
in a bit of a hurry‐‐
[SAORI yelps]
Miss Fujiko. Look at this!
[FUJIKO]
Next generation idols.
The "Staring‐at‐Eye Moles
Squad?" What is that?
[KITA] You're so in! Those
moles of yours are perfect!
Moles under the eyes
aren't an uncommon feature.
But color, size, location.
It takes an exquisite balance
of all these factors to create
a unique and charming look.
[FUJIKO]
I'd never thought of that.
My name is Kita,
and I'm with Star Promotions.
Here's my card.
Ah. Thank you.
[KITA] We're debuting the group
with a public audition next week
at the Kabukicho Festival.
But you've already passed, so
you'll be performing that day.
Which means we'll need
you to work on your singing
and dancing for the next week.
We've arranged daily training
sessions from 2 to 6 PM,
and we're going to need
you to attend all of them.
[FUJIKO whimpers]
[SAORI]
You can leave that to me!
Don't worry about the store,
I'll take care of everything.
[FUJIKO]
I shouldn't.
Please. Let me do this.
I know that you've always
wanted to be an idol.
So go! Make
your dreams come true!
[gasps]
[FUJIKO] The week
went by before I knew it.
I sang and danced my heart out!
Until at long last, the day
came for my big debut.
But then...
I tried calling Star Promotions
just a little while ago.
They told me
that there's nobody
working there named Kita.
And now I don't
know where he's gone.
I beg you, help me
find Mister Kita.
‐‐[KOBAYASHI] Aww...
‐‐[FUJIKO] I... I just...
I really wanna be an idol!
[ALL groan]
Well, anyone have questions?
Have you talked to your
parents about becoming an idol?
They might have some
advice that could help.
I wish I'd had the chance.
Miss Fujiko lost her
parents at an early age.
She's been keeping that flower
shop going all by herself!
That part‐timer
Saori is working there.
What's some
retired cabaret girl know
about doing actual work?
[FUJIKO] That's not fair,
Saori's a total sweetheart.
Are you staying at a hotel?
I am. I was
planning on checking in
after the audition
this afternoon.
It's too late for them
to refund my reservation,
so Saori told me to just
stay there and leave
the shop to her.
Not a whole lot
to this one, is there?
I wouldn't be too
sure about that.
There's more going on
than you might think.
If you say so, old man.
After the sun has set
upon the rest of the world.
We turn our thoughts to
the hopes and dreams
of a young maiden.
These detectives'
hearts brim with compassion
in this tenement where
tears fall like rain.
The humble building
that people call
the Detectives' Row House.
Mwah.
One million yen
to the one who finds
our dear friend Kita.
[HUDSON]
Ready... Go!
[KOBAYASHI]
Miss Fujiko.
I swear, I won't rest
until you become an idol.
Huh...?
[yells]
[gasps]
Wait, Mister Holmes.
What about your injury?
It was a minor fracture.
I'm still able to walk.
[WATSON sighs]
Poor boy.
I wonder if he's even
noticed that Sherlock
has been training him.
Yeah. Sherlock never lets
anybody into his room.
You're right.
I don't think a single person
has managed to make
their way in except for James.
[SHERLOCK] Finish the dishes
and then get the laundry going.
[WATSON]
Uh‐huh.
[SHERLOCK] And don't let
anybody into my room.
Not a soul.
[sighs]
‐‐[grunts]
‐‐[doorbell rings]
[MARY] Hi, John.
You're in there, right?
[music plays loudly]
[music cuts out]
[thumping]
[running footsteps]
Hello, sir!
Next time, just ring the
bell if you need someone.
Get me a cyclamen.
Sorry, but, could you
point me to that?
[MAN]
You are a florist, aren't you?
I'm just the part‐time help.
Right now,
you're no help at all!
If it's not on the shelves,
then it's sold out.
[SAORI]
Thank you, please come again.
[receiver ringing]
[WATSON]
Hello, Watson speaking.
[SHERLOCK] Don't let
the phone ring that long.
[WATSON]
The dishes are all done,
and I'm working
on the laundry now.
Our culprit. It's Saori.
[SHERLOCK]
Our culprit, it's Saori.
Uh. Okay, but who's Saori?
[SHERLOCK]
The part‐timer at the florist!
I sent you a picture.
[SHERLOCK] My shelves
have information on locals
with records, and
this girl's got one.
Figure out who her partner
is and send me a picture.
Now.
[cell phone ringing]
[SHERLOCK]
Hmph.
Hey.
Care to tell me
why you've been
staring at that woman?
What? Sherlock?
You're my rival on this case,
so I'm not going to answer that.
[MARY whimpers]
Was it him?
[WATSON humming]
What did I say?
Sorry, who are you?
Hi, Mr. Holmes!
You let Mary
in here, didn't you?
[WATSON]
No, of course not.
All we did was chat
on the doorstep for a bit.
Is that bad?
[grunts]
What are you holding?
Oh! Mr. Holmes, please!
Whatever I did, I'm sorry!
Stop it!
You don't have to do‐‐
[WATSON]
Ah. What is that?
It's a wire. Get out of here.
And don't ever let me
see your face again.
[WATSON whimpers]
[BOY 2A laughs]
I won!
[BOY 2B]
Seriously?
[GIRL 2A]
You must have good karma.
[BOY 2A]
I had it comin'.
[BOY 2D] Yeah, they banned me
from that pachinko place...
[GIRL 2B]
Mister?
‐‐[BOY 2B] You did that?
‐‐[GIRL 2A] What a hero!
Chocolate's always
nice when you're sad.
You're sweet. Much obliged.
[MORIARTY]
Don't eat that.
The Irregulars loaded
it with tranquilizers.
In ten seconds
you'd be out like a light.
What's your problem?
[YOSHIO]
Get lost.
Yeah, we had him
till you screwed it up.
Why don'tcha mind
yer damn business...
Leave the poor guy alone.
Yoshio already got his wallet
when he first showed up.
Wait. I remember you.
If ya been cleaned
out, go home already.
[BOY 2D]
Screw this, let's hit the slots.
Yeah!
[BOY 2D] Best way to
spend other people's money!
Lemme up on your shoulders.
[MORIARTY] So I'm guessing this
is your first time in Kabukicho?
That's right.
I only moved into my place over
on the West Side a year ago.
[MORIARTY] You should watch your
back in this part of town.
Officially, it's all Shinjuku,
but this side of the wall
might as well be
a different country.
You've probably caught
on to that by now.
And Kabukicho here
is the heart of the jungle.
People look at a Westsider
like you and see an easy mark.
Fair enough.
[MORIARTY] I hear Sherlock
kicked you out of the storeroom.
[WATSON grunts]
[MORIARTY] Why were you
trying to hire him, anyway?
[WATSON] Because I've stumbled
into a dangerous situation.
[MORIARTY] But there are
plenty of detectives around.
Right, and I did think
about that, but once I met him,
I knew that nobody
else could help.
I think he's someone
I can trust.
[MORIARTY]
Let me give you a little tip.
[MORIARTY chuckles]
Do kids even go for the whole
eye‐mole thing anymore?
Of course not, dummy,
the audition was a scam
from the start.
Oh, yeah. That's inconspicuous.
[LUCY]
Let's go.
[MARY]
Where's he even going?
[BOTH gasp]
[MARY]
He went this way!
[MARY gasps]
Behind us!
[MARY panting]
[LUCY pantin]
How the hell does
he keep slipping away?!
[panting]
[LUCY yells]
[MARY]
Did you catch him?
[YOSHIO groans]
Crap, they got us.
[elephant trumpets]
[YOSHIO] Sorry boutcha.
But you're outta time.
[groans]
[KITA, SAORI grunting]
How did you catch us?
You want to know?
I do.
You're sure?
I'm sure. So let's hear it.
[SHERLOCK chuckles]
I tell ya, the kids these days
are into some weird crap!
Oh boy, what is it now?
What, you haven't heard?
Fujiko from the flower shop
got picked up as an idol!
Who'd a' thought?
Eh, that whole
thing was horse shit.
Well, that's a
little harsh, isn't it?
I mean, she's not
much to look at, sure,
but she's a sweet girl!
Not her, ya dummy.
I'm saying the
audition was a con.
But what's the point of
planning a whole fake audition?
That's a fair question.
Y'see, there's this
girl named Saori.
Ah, you mean the part‐timer
from the flower shop?
Yeah, but the
problem is she doesn't
know anything about flowers.
I went there to
pick up a cyclamen
and she said they'd sold out.
So? Shops sell out
of stuff sometimes.
But they couldn't have
sold out of cyclamen
at this time of year.
It's a winter flower.
Ooh! There's a shock for ya!
And what's more,
she came out front with
little bits of concrete dust
all over her clothes.
All those song and dance
lessons were just a trick
to get Fujiko out of
the shop every day.
So that Saori could smash
a hole through the back wall
into the alley, and guess
what's behind the place?
[gasps]
The Bentendou pawn shop!
No doubt there's plenty
there worth stealing,
but busting a hole
through the wall seems
a little much, don'tcha think?
Here's the twist:
That Kita guy
who ran the auditions
also goes by another name.
Kitaro the Mongoose.
Ooh! Oh! I know that name!
That's right.
The Mongoose was once the rival
of the bank robber called Cobra.
And he knew that Bentendou
was where Cobra used
to clean up the filthy
lucre from his heists.
You're saying the idol
gimmick was just a trick
Saori and Kita came up with to
lure poor plain‐jane Fujiko
out of her shop so they could
bust into Cobra's secret stash?
Precisely. So what's
a desperate idol have
in common with a guy
caught robbing a pawn shop?
Why don'tcha tell me?
In the end, both of
'em are gonna get screwed.
[SHERLOCK] Thanks for
coming out, that's the show.
[COBRA laughing]
[KITA gasps]
You're Cobra.
Hello, Sherlock Holmes.
And goodbye.
[SHERLOCK grunts]
[COBRA groans]
[SAORI gasps]
[gasps]
[WATSON pantin]
Why are you here?
[WATSON] Phew. I'm glad
I made it in time.
You did not solve it!
You're nothing more than
a good‐natured bumpkin!
My inductive reasoning
is far beyond the faculties...
You know, I did
just save your life.
[KOBAYASHI] Would this be a good
place for the moth orchid?
Sure. Thanks
so much for your help.
[KOBAYASHI whimpers]
Anytime!
I'll be your biggest fan till
the day I die, Miss Fujiko.
[FUJIKO giggles]
[FUYUTO]
Damn it!
So the bank offered
a twenty million yen reward
for the stolen bullion?
Sherlock Holmes,
you're one lucky bastard.
[MARY groans] I don't know how
I'm supposed to keep
‐‐going like this.
‐‐You've had enough barley tea.
I'm gonna have to cut you off.
[MARY]
Mm?
Mary. You planted a bug on me.
[MARY giggles]
Sorry 'bout that.
Well, I... All I want
to say to you is that‐‐
[LUCY]
I'm interested to hear this.
This conversation only
concerns me and Mary.
I know you're worried,
as her brother, but still,
that doesn't give you
the right to involve‐‐
Her sister.
Ah.
Not her brother.
You got me?
Yes! My apologies.
[PIPE yowls, hisses]
[WATSON whimpers]
[WATSON whimperin]
[PIPE growls]
[WATSON whimpers]
[WATSON squeals]
[screaming]
Hey, you guys.
[WATSON gasps]
[MORIARTY]
Hmm?
So he did have help.
Stay out of my business.
I couldn't just
walk away and leave him
moping alone on that bench.
[WATSON sigh]
It's still funny how
you're always latching
onto some weird case.
Wait, he is?
[MORIARTY] Yeah. Let's
see, there was that one
he took a while back
where that snake fell down
out of the ceiling.
Really. As it happens,
when I was
working at that university
hospital on the West Side,
I was autopsying
a certain young girl's body
when a pit viper suddenly‐‐
Shut up and fold.
[WATSON groans]
Back to moping.
You hate to see it.
[gasps]
[MORIARTY]
Chin up.
So... We've met, but
I'm James Moriarty.
[B‐ZO] Great! Always
love to meet a fan, my baby.