My son James must
be held accountable
for the crime that he committed.
But please... Know this.
He only wanted justice!
[sobs]
[CROWD murmuring]
So Jack the Ripper hid
from the cops for months,
only to get merc'd
by some teenager?
Holy shit.
Yeah, what he did was wrong,
but I still think he's hot!
James Moran,
the son of ward mayor
Sebastian Moran, is awaiting
trial for the murder of
serial killer Jack the Ripper.
Jack, who has been
living in Kabukicho under
an assumed identity,
was assumed in the deaths
of Alexandra Moran...
[IRENE]
So...
James got his revenge for Alex.
Tell me, Irene.
Did you already know him?
Before he left for
the East Side, I mean.
Yes.
I met him when I was
working as Alex's tutor.
Whoa! [British accent]
Spot o' tea?
That sounds perfect!
[IRENE]
She was sickly and frail,
so much that she could
rarely leave her room.
And then, the day
she finally managed
to get out of the house,
she was murdered by Jack.
I couldn't believe
it was a coincidence.
It seemed like
Mayor Moran might be hiding
some connection
to Jack the Ripper.
And that's why you decided
to steal the USB drive.
[IRENE]
Exactly.
You were right to be suspicious.
Moran had been hiring
Jack to take out anyone
who stood in his way.
The data on his USB drive
was proof of that.
But Jack destroyed the drive,
meaning we have no concrete
evidence tying Moran to any of
the crimes he committed.
I guess Alex was just a casualty
of whatever they were up to.
Yeah. It seems that way.
[IRENE sighs]
‐‐[phone buzzes]
‐‐Ah.
[IRENE]
Well, I'm going back inside.
[buzzing continues]
Thank you. I'm glad to
at least have a bit of closure.
[IRENE]
It's me.
Good to hear from you.
Yeah.
Really?
We're still the only ones
who have the whole story.
Aren't you going to tell
Irene and the others?
It's not my call.
Moriarty didn't want
anyone to know.
Give it to me.
Please, Sherlock Holmes.
[SHERLOCK sighs]
Yeah, but why?
He was a target.
His own father tried
to have him killed.
What could drive someone
to do that to his child?
We'll never know
the answer to that question.
That might be for the best.
I'm guessing that Moriarty
didn't want to know, either.
Hey, old man, you look like
ya got a lot on your mind.
It doesn't make sense
no matter how I look at it.
Moriarty had no reason
to kill Jack like that.
He had a knife in his hand,
and the guy who
murdered his sister was
right in front of him.
I think anyone
would go kinda nuts.
‐‐Ugh. But still...
‐‐[WATSON] I get it.
Sherlock.
You're worried about
Moriarty, aren't you?
No, of course not.
That kid's not my‐‐
It's fine. I understand.
I'm worried about him, too,
and you've known him
way longer than me.
Seriously, I'm not
worried about him.
Your best friend's
in jail for murder.
What you're going
through right now‐‐
‐‐I can't even imagine.
‐‐Slow down.
I mean, the whole thing
is unbelievable.
‐‐Watso‐‐
‐‐He killed someone!
[SHERLOCK sighs]
Aren't you going to go back to
your life on the West Side now?
Jack's dead and
the USB drive was destroyed.
Moran has no reason
to come after you anymore.
That's true.
I could go back if I wanted...
[phone rings]
[SHERLOCK]
We got a job.
[HUDSON]
My Pipe, my li'l floof...
My baby!
[sobs]
I could just die!
I'm literally dying right now!
[HUDSON]
My Pipe...
[sobs]
My precious furbaby...
He disappeared last night
and he still hasn't come home!
I raised him from
a kitten and he's never done
anything like this
in his whole life!
And what's worse, there's
a catnapper running around!
This creep's been
seen stealing pets
from all over Kabukicho and
selling them at crazy prices.
What if he got
his hands on my Pipe?
From a business standpoint,
it's probably not worth the
hassle to boost a cat that size.
Sorry, but I still
can't get my mind off
everything with Morty.
I thought I knew him, but now...
Yeah, and Maki.
This sucks!
Jack played us all for fools.
That bastard got exactly
what he deserved!
Ugh. Your next job
is to bring my sweet boy home!
I'm not making an offer,
I'm giving an order! Got it?!
[MICHEL] That's how we're
doing things now?
[HUDSON] After the sun has set
upon the rest of the world,
our little town of Kabukicho
lights up in neon.
If gold and silver
are what you're after,
then we can talk about
other work once you find
my goddamn cat!
A light gleams
in these detectives' eyes.
This is a haven for
outcasts and oddballs.
And you're the reason they call
it "the Detectives' Row House!"
We've got a new rank
for this job: A‐Five, top grade!
Whoever brings my Pipe home will
be treated to the finest beef
upon God's green Earth.
Ready...
Go!
‐‐[MICHEL sighs] Buncha shit...
‐‐Lame.
[sighing]
[sighs]
[gasps]
Thank you, dear.
Things are getting heavy.
I think we could all use
a bit of levity right now.
[HUDSON]
Hmm.
[FUYUTO whimpers]
It's not true, right?
My Maki... is Jack?
There's no way. Right?
Maki.
Tell them they're
wrong about you.
Tell me it's not true.
[sobs]
Maki...
[LUCY]
Pipe's missing.
Aren't you gonna go
help look for him?
[MARY sniffs]
This whole time...
...Morty was dealing with
his sister's murder.
And I...
I never even noticed
anything was wrong!
He was bearing it
all by himself.
But she's my sister,
the only one I've got.
[LUCY]
You understand, don't you?
Since you've got a sister, too.
Yeah, I get it.
[sobbing]
[LUCY] I've got a few things
to say to that kid
when he gets back.
"Look here, jackass!
We're your friends and
we all wanna help you!"
Ya know?
[LUCY] When he comes home,
you'll be here
waiting for him, right?
Of course.
So in the meantime,
let's just worry
about the job that's
in front of us.
We gotta go find Pipe.
[MARY]
Heh.
[sighs] Why waste
my time working a case
that's not gonna
pay a single yen?
Right? You see where
I'm coming from.
Meow.
‐‐[pachinko beeping]
‐‐[MICHEL] Huh?
The hits keep on coming.
[GAMBLER 12A]
Hey, Michel!
Havin' a good one, are ya?
[MICHEL]
Doin' all right.
[GAMBLER 12B] I've been hearing
talk that Jack the Ripper
was a regular at Pipe Cat.
Could you tell me if
there's any truth to that?
And I heard that the kid
who took him out,
Moran's son, he was
there all the time, too.
Is that right?
[MICHEL]
Yep.
[GAMBLER 12B] That's a hell
of a thing for the Mayor
to have to deal with.
[GAMBLER 12A]
On the news, they're saying
he wanted revenge
for his sister,
but she's still dead,
and now he's a murderer.
‐‐[MICHEL growls]
‐‐Something wrong?
I don't have a kind
word to say about Moran.
Not one.
But I know exactly what
it's like to lose a daughter
to murder, and I know
more than anything,
he'd want her killer gone.
Are you trying to tell me
his son did him wrong?
[GAMBLERS sigh]
[pachinko balls clattering]
[PIPE meows]
‐‐Ah!
‐‐Jackpot!
[GAMBLER 12F]
That cat hit it big!
Back off, ya freeloaders!
Hey!
[growls]
I'll skin that damn cat.
Make me a shamisen!
[JURI]
What's with the baby carriage?
[YOSHIO]
Tacky.
I needed one
that Pipe would fit in.
That was the biggest they had.
Someday you'll have bills
to pay, too, ya little gremlins.
When are we gonna
see the captain again?
I'm bored.
I hope he's back soon.
[KOBAYASHI growls]
Hey! Stop whining and
do something useful!
Moriarty's not here right now,
so the Irregulars have
to take care of things
while he's gone, get it?
[KIDS gasping]
So until it's time
for him to come home,
‐‐I guess Yoshio's the new boss!
‐‐[KIDS gasping]
It's your job
to watch over Kabukicho.
[gasping]
So I'm... in charge?
Heh. Kobayashi.
Mrs. Hudson has everybody out
looking for Pipe, right?
Yeah. She's had
a rough couple of days,
considering the way
everything went down
with Moriarty and
Maki and all that.
The least we can do for her
is track down her cat.
‐‐[YOSHIO] Hmm...
‐‐[KOBAYASHI] Hm?
Right! Irregulars.
As acting captain, my first
order is to ditch Kobayashi
and find Pipe ourselves!
[KIDS]
Roger!
Hey, wait a minute! I thought
you were gonna help me!
Heh.
[KOBAYASHI]
Ugh...
[SHERLOCK chuckling]
Hey, Sherlock?
You do realize that you
have a case to work on.
[SHERLOCK growls]
I'm not missing Thomas Shomaru's
final performance
to go chase Pipe.
Heh. Especially after I got
the very last ticket they had!
[WATSON]
Really?
I don't think anyone is excited
about playing cat catcher,
but I still think we
should help Mrs. Hudson out.
Eh. Don't let me stop y‐‐
‐‐[PIPE meows]
‐‐[SHERLOCK gasps]
[PIPE purring]
[PIPE meows]
You furry little bastard!
[WATSON]
Sherlock!
Hang on...
[MARY] Would Pipe really
be in a place like this?
[LUCY] Well, one of the guys out
front said he saw a giant cat
head inside there earlier.
There can't be that
many running around.
[GIRLS squealing, talking]
How cute! Hey guys,
let me take a selfie!
[yelps]
[MARY snarls]
He's heading your way!
Get ready, Lu!
[crashing, clattering]
[LUCY grunts]
‐‐[PIPE meows]
‐‐You're mine!
‐‐[MARY groans]
‐‐[LUCY gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
So that's where we're at.
[FUJIKO] Uhh... Well, sorry,
but I haven't seen Pipe.
Maybe this could help you out?
Here, on the house.
[KOBAYASHI]
Great, what is it?
It's an herb that
cats go crazy for.
The scent could bring
Pipe straight to you.
‐‐It's yours!
‐‐Ahh!
Ms. Fujiko, my angel!
[SHERLOCK] Sorry, old man,
but I seriously don't think
the cat's been looking
at that guidebook.
The tubby little
beast is a lot faster
than you'd think.
There's no way we're gonna
bring him in unless we come up
with a solid plan first.
So we check
the hottest cat meet‐up spots?
Maybe he hit up some back‐alley
dumpster only the locals know.
Pfft. Patience is
a virtue, my friend.
Especially when I already
know where he's headed.
What he's really
after is dessert.
‐‐[yelps]
‐‐[WATSON] Watch out!
[sighs]
Please, pay attention
to the signal.
After all the ways you
could have died by now,
are you really going
to wander into traffic?
[SHERLOCK]
Hmph.
[WATSON] Anyway, you were
saying something about a plan
to track down Pipe?
I hear that luthiers
sometimes use stolen cats
to build shamisen.
So we should probably work fast.
[SHERLOCK]
All I want is my ticket back.
Pipe could end up as a shamisen
or a junior‐size fur coat
as far as I'm concerned.
Oh, come on.
I know you don't mean that.
You have some attachment
to that monster?
To be honest,
I think he's kind of a jerk.
He refused to let me sleep
anywhere in the bar that time,
and when we threw that birthday
party for Moriarty, I spent
the whole night guarding
my cake from the cat.
But something about
him makes him hard to hate.
Ah. Hold on!
[YOSHIO]
Where's that stupid cat?
Maybe someone else
found him already.
[gasps]
Look!
Was that... Kobayashi?
‐‐[PIPE meows]
‐‐[gasping]
[chuckling]
Ugh... How's that
fat cat so good at hiding?
Wait, what?
You're looking for this cat?
[MICHEL]
I'll be right back!
[COP 12A]
Mr. Belmont!
[KIDS] Kobayashi!
We're taking that cat!
[THIEF 12A grunts]
[YOSHIO]
Huh...? Wait, who is this?
‐‐[LYCHEE, RENKO gasp]
‐‐[PARROT 12A] Craw!
[YOSHIO] That's the parrot
from the tobacco shop!
‐‐[CATS meowing]
‐‐[laughs] It's too much!
[laughing]
Help me, Fujiko!
Now. We're gonna jump
him on the count of three.
[MARY]
Mm.
[LUCY, MARY]
One...
‐‐[MICHEL] That shamisen...
‐‐[MARY] Michy?!
...is miine!
Ahh!
[MARY]
Argh! What are you doing?!
Mrow!
Mew!
Mraw!
[PIPE]
Meeoow!
[WATSON]
All right, we got him!
Awesome plan, Sherlock!
Uh. Sherlock?
‐‐Hey.
‐‐You wanna hear?
I mean... I kind of
helped you do it, so, uh‐‐
Yes or no.
Ah. Of course. Please.
[giggles]
Old man!
Word's been getting around that
you were the one who brought in
the monster cat of Kabukicho!
So what kinda magic
power did you use, huh?
Nothing magic
about it, my friend.
After all, there's only one
way for a cat to wind up
as fat as Pipe.
[MICHEL]
It's all come together.
[WATSON, SHERLOCK]
Hm?
That chubby little furball is
the biggest gourmand
in Kabukicho.
Of course, he's gonna
seek out the best food
the city has to offer.
And he's not gonna
stop after the first meal.
Obviously, he'll hit up every
three‐star restaurant in town
before he's done.
[SHERLOCK growls] Ugh. Anyway,
a classy cat like Pipe knows
that no proper dinner is
complete without dessert.
You do realize
he licks his own crotch?
And besides,
dessert could have been
a million different things.
So how did you figure out‐‐
[YOSHIO]
He likes strawberries!
So we went all over town
getting as many as we could!
You mean to tell me
that you guys put down
trails of strawberries
from every restaurant
in the whole city to
lure him to this park?
Jeez, a kid could
have come up with that plan.
[SHERLOCK]
Argh!
So that's what you
meant when you said
patience is a virtue.
You're one smart fella!
Although, I still don't
see how you figured out
strawberries are
what Pipe likes.
Oh. Well that's simple.
‐‐[MARY] Right here!
‐‐Augh!
From Moriarty's birthday.
‐‐[MARY] See?
‐‐Hey, that's right!
In fact...
And when we threw that
birthday party for Moriarty,
I spent the whole night
guarding my cake
from the cat.
But he's hard to hate.
Ah. Hold on!
Well, now it seems obvious.
Screw you all!
I don't have time for this!
Give it. Gimme
the ticket right now‐‐
‐‐[yelps]
‐‐[PIPE yowls]
He's making
a break for it, you guys!
[WATSON gasps, yelps]
[groans]
[PIPE purring]
Hi there, Pipe!
[PIPE gagging]
[WATSON groans]
[SHERLOCK gasps]
[SHERLOCK screams]
Welcome back, Pipe,
my furry darling.
Here's to you!
And to you kiddos for
catching that nasty pet thief.
Excellent work!
Enough drama!
It's time to party!
I hope you're ready
to stuff your faces silly,
because I've got enough
top‐grade meat for everybody.
[ALL]
All right!
Lift those glasses!
Cheers!
[ALL]
[laughing, chatting]
[sobbing]
[MARY]
You just don't get it, do you?
‐‐[IRENE chuckles]
‐‐Mrowr?
Sorry. About the show, I mean.
[SHERLOCK]
Hmph.
You know, I, um...
I just wanna say,
the time I've spent here,
it's been a lot more interesting
than it was on the West Side.
Getting to see all of you work.
Making new friends.
So... Um...
The thing is... I want
to stay and be your assistant.
Huh?!
You might not like
to admit it, but you need me.
Screw up once and
I'll fire you on the spot.
Oh, come on.
We'll have fun.
[MARY laughs]
What's this?
You're finally
making it official?
Jeez, Sherlock, you're not gonna
leave the guy hanging, are you?
[SHERLOCK]
Pfft. Yeah, I am.
‐‐[WATSON] Huh?! Hey. Sherlock!
‐‐[MARY] Fine. Hey!
Get this, everyone!
Watson and Sherlock
made it official.
Isn't that great?
Let's hear it
for the happy couple!
‐‐[laughter]
‐‐[MARY] Aren't they adorable?
[SHERLOCK]
You're leaving?
[IRENE groans]
I left a note for Mrs. Hudson
explaining things.
I didn't want to ruin the fun.
It's quite the party.
I'm going to New York.
Norton says that he's found some
new way to make a killing there.
Yes! Future!
[VOICE 12A]
Greetings from New York.
Norton here, with my next gift
for the men of the world.
[VOICE 12A]
New York!
If you're looking for lov‐‐
I should be heading out now.
Wouldn't want to
miss my flight, would I?
You're not going
to try to stop me?
[gasps]
[IRENE]
Just kidding.
Well... Goodbye, Sherlock.
[MYCROFT]
I believe I made it clear
that you have no right
to refer to me that way.