[WATSON grunts]
[WATSON]
The East Side.
Kabukicho.
The city of chaos.
So where is it?
[MAN 1A]
Hey, bruh.
You a boss at home,
or a boss out here?
C'mon, man, you gotta
be a boss somewhere, right?
Uh. Uh...
I guess at home, but I‐‐
My man!
I get it, married life
can be a grind,
and our girls don't judge.
Um, actually. I'm looking
for the Pipe Cat.
Huh?
A job?
Yes.
Okay. Where is it?
[MAN 1A] Follow the paw
prints and you're there.
[CAT 1A]
Mrowr?
♪
♪ Quit wasting all
your time and money, yeah ♪
♪ And solve a
pink heart mystery ♪
♪ In a jungle bursting
with danger and ♪
♪ the biggest fears
you've ever seen ♪
♪ Oh, darling, don't be shy ♪
♪ You're in for a night ♪
♪ Why not take it slow ♪
♪ Gentlemen, I fear it's
about to get hot here ♪
♪ Ladies of means can go home ♪
♪ Welcome to Kabukicho ♪
♪ We're waiting for you
at 221st Avenue ♪
♪ It's a magical wonderland
for boys and more ♪
♪ A little row house
a touch out of this world ♪
♪ Pipe Cat ♪
Come up and see me sometime.
Perfect, you boys are good!
[HUDSON] Do it just like that
at the show tomorrow, darlings.
Thank you!
Oh, my. Here's a face
I haven't seen before.
Call me Mrs. Hudson.
Mwah!
[WATSON whimpers]
Yes, ah, nice to meet you.
I heard that I might be able
to find a detective here?
[bell rings
[HUDSON]
Oh.
So are we missing anybody?
[HUDSON] Hmm...
Only three made it out
'cause it's short notice.
You, darling,
park those buns and relax.
[wails]
Sorry, could I‐‐
[GIRLS gasping]
Are you thirsty?
'Cause I am just parched.
No. Actually I came here for‐‐
‐‐You need a drink. Right?
‐‐[MAKI] Mm.
[CHINKILL] Come on, have
a seat, take the edge off.
‐‐Let's chat.
‐‐[DIANE] You new in town?
Inspector Lestrade.
What have we got today?
It seems, our boy is back at it.
It's Jack the Ripper.
[gasping]
[GREGORY] A dead body was
found in an empty condo
about an hour ago.
[FUYUTO] And we know
that it was him for a fact?
Yes, this crime
scene was Jack to a T.
Up until now, your
department's been doing
everything in their
power to keep us
away from the Jack case.
So why the change of heart?
Call it righteous rage.
We've been chasing
after him for months
and people are still
turning up dead.
To hell with
the department pride,
I want this thing solved!
Ah...
Ward Mayor Moran.
Jack murdered his
daughter six months ago,
so he has a personal interest.
After watching the police
fumble the case
for so long, he's
turning to us to try
and give him some closure.
These eyes of mine
can't be fooled.
Well. In any case,
we should get to the crime scene
before the press shows up.
[FUYUTO]
What's the pay rank on this?
S with a great
big cherry on top.
A cool ten mill.
After the sun has set
upon the rest of the world,
our town of Kabukicho
lights up in neon.
If gold and silver
are what you're after,
then solve this mystery
before your peers do!
This is a haven for
outcasts and oddballs.
And you boys are
the reason they call it
"the Detectives' Row House."
Mwah!
Now, get down on your marks.
Ten million yen to the first man
who catches Jack the Ripper.
Ready...
Go!
I'm sayin' that's your
whole problem, ya putz!
Right. I'll work on it.
Ahh!
Sorry...
Ah, no.
Uh.
[KOBAYASHI panting]
Hey, has it started yet?
[MICHEL] We're finally going
after Jack the Ripper.
Ah! Come on!
That's the biggest case
we've gotten in forever!
He said Jack?
Sir, are you Mister Holmes?
Bite your tongue.
I will not abide being
mistaken for that freak!
Ah! Beg your pardon.
Now, then.
Fame and fortune and a place
on the West Side await!
[MAKI]
Huh...?
[whimpers] I can hear the
case calling out to me.
Ladies.
[CHINKILL] Tch. Yeah, well,
you better go answer it,
ya big weirdo.
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI sobbing]
Wait, is your name
Sherlock Holmes?
No.
[WATSON growls]
I need your help.
Sir, I'm begging you,
please just hear me out!
Just give me five minutes.
That's all I ask.
You're him, right?
You're the only one
who can help me! Please!
[gasps] Um. Boss Kaneko told
me I would find you here.
Mr. Holmes?
[BOY 1A grunts] Hey, watch where
you're walking, you idiot!
Sorry.
I looked at the engine‐‐
turns out a spark plug
had come loose.
Let's talk. I can drive you.
My name is John Watson.
I work at a university
hospital on the West Side,
and I need your help.
Some strange things have been
happening to me lately.
You name the price.
Whatever you ask for,
I'll pay it.
And how to plan to pay?
[WATSON gasps]
That kid!
This is Shinjuku
Ward's east side.
Kabukicho.
[SHERLOCK] And one step
beyond these neon borders
lies the darkness.
[GREGORY] The victim's
name is Sayuri Onoue.
We found fingerprints we
believe belonged to the killer,
but we ran them
against our database
and didn't find a match.
[FUYUTO whimpers]
‐‐[yelps]
‐‐Good effort.
Please get out of the way.
Genitals have been removed.
Angel wings drawn
in blood around the body.
It does look like Jack's work.
What would you say,
four, five hours?
[FUYUTO] The current stage
of rigor mortis would indicate
no less than six
hours since death.
Kyogoku Fuyuto's
eyes cannot be fooled.
This poor girl
died far too young.
Great Buddha preserve us.
[FUYUTO] Inspector, could we
see the victim's cell phone?
[GREGORY]
Bring it in.
Ahh, Mr. Holmes, please proceed.
[MICHEL] Well, you certainly did
take your time getting here.
[MICHEL]
Who are you?
I'm his driver. Hello.
[MICHEL]
Hmm.
It looks like the uterine
body and cervix
have been fully extracted,
but the job wasn't
done very cleanly.
[sniffs]
Say, do you smell what I smell?
Yeah.
I'd say Bahamas.
You'd say Ba‐huh?
So, who is he talking to?
Can't tell. Probably
either Hatsu or Kuma.
[SHERLOCK sighs]
Where is her phone?
I just handed it to Kyogoku.
Oh. Apologies.
All yours.
This condo is
currently unoccupied,
and it's hard to imagine the
girl came here all by herself.
She didn't have any
messages instructing her
to come, either, so it seems
likely that Jack brought
her up personally.
Hold on! What are
you trying to pull?!
[FEMALE VOICE] Hello, gentlemen!
Welcome to the White Rose.
To make a reservation,
please leave a message with
the desired date and time‐‐
[GREGORY] Ah! You have
to quit doing things
like that, Sherlock!
It appears that the victim
took off her clothes willingly.
It stands to reason that
they knew each other
and agreed to meet up here.
Yeah, I'm with you.
[FUYUTO] Hah! These eyes
of mine can already see
how this case is going to end!
Gentlemen.
Well, then. Friends,
we have a lead to follow up on.
Where are we?
Don't get out much, I take it.
We're at the White Rose.
The biggest cabaret
club in all of Kabukicho.
The owner's a former
host named Masaya.
Word around town is the
man personally interviews
all the girls here and
then sleeps with
the ones he likes the best.
And it only gets
worse from there.
[WOMEN] It's lovely
to meet you boys! Hi!
All right, we'll put
everything on this.
Okay, you got it!
Heh!
[MICHEL] Hm? When
we're on a case with
a special bonus like this,
the client covers all expenses.
Dining and
entertainment included.
It's a nice little perk.
[WOMAN 1B] Hmm? Hey now,
I can make that for you.
[SHERLOCK gulps]
How about some drinks for us?
[belches]
Do you know Sayuri Onoue?
Uh. No. We don't know
each other's real names.
Bring someone who does.
Come on. Nobody likes
talking about work, right?
Mm? Uh. Sorry.
Cosmetic blepharoplasty on
the upper eyelids, hyaluronic
acid fillers under the eyes,
and a bit of a nose job.
My compliments to the surgeon.
I smell traces of
benzalkonium chloride
and chlorhexidine gluconate
mixed with your body's odor.
Hmph. You've been
turning tricks to pay off
the loan for your surgery.
[growls]
I'm done with this.
[sighs]
You had to chase her off.
Is just a moment of fun
really too much to ask?
At this moment, yes.
[HOST 1A]
Sir.
I'll have to ask you to leave.
Do you know
the name Sayuri Onoue?
[HOST 1A]
No. Now kindly get out.
East Side Police
Detective Lestrade's
younger sister.
[gasps]
[MICHEL] We already know
that she received a call
from this place three days ago.
If Lestrade heard you were
hiding something about
his beloved little sister,
he'd be so angry that wig
of his would catch fire.
[HOST 1A]
This is a legitimate business.
Nobody is forcing any of
our girls to do anything.
Hey, there it is.
Looks like we
interviewed her,
but in the end, the
boss turned her down.
That's what we know.
Sorry to disappoint you.
[doorbell rings]
[gasps]
And you must be Mattsun.
Huh?
Your forbidden love
affair has taken quite
the turn tonight,
wouldn't you say?
Ah? Forbidden? Don't judge me.
I'm only trying to do what
my heart tells me!
How vile.
Defiling the body that way.
Your heart is a twisted
one indeed.
[MATTSUN]
Hey, back off!
[FUYUTO]
According to her phone records,
you were in contact with
the woman one month ago.
Which is plenty of time to
decide on her as your target.
You did it! Right, Jack?
[MATTSUN]
Huh? Uh, Jack? Who is Jack?
This is all my fault.
I just... I couldn't
let you go, Mattsun.
Norio.
Don't you dare start talking
like this was a mistake!
[sobs]
I know our love is right!
[NORIO, MATTSUN sobbing]
That "forbidden love" line
prob'ly came off really bad.
Yeah... sorry...
[sobbing continues]
[door creaks]
[SHERLOCK] Right. Then
I suppose I'll keep waiting.
[SHERLOCK]
Of course.
I'd also prefer not to
get the police involved.
'Bye.
Do you know how to knock?
[WATSON] I apologize, but I
really need you to take my case.
I suppose you found your wallet.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[stomach growls]
[microwave dings]
[WATSON whimpers]
[HUDSON]
Hi, James!
I'll be up later with the
crème puffs I got for you.
[MORIARTY]
Thank you!
Hey there.
Great, I found you.
Ya dropped this.
[WATSON grunts]
[MORIARTY]
Thought I should help you out,
since you're Sherlock's
client and all.
I spent the money.
Bought food for
a buncha poor kids.
[gasps]
He's not my client.
[MORIARTY] I heard Jack
the Ripper showed up again.
That's fun, right?
I know you've solved the case.
So let's hear the whole story.
[SHERLOCK grunts]
[chuckles]
Hey, how ya been?!
Who's that? Ah, Kuma.
Good to see ya!
Even if you always kinda look
like someone ran over your dog!
That's a hell of a way
to greet someone
in his own home.
Sit down and get comfortable!
So, what's your take?
Well, I couldn't help but
notice that the guy had missed
a button on his clothes,
which means...
[gasps]
...it was the lover who done it!
No. The girl's lover
had no part in all this.
Huh? How ya figure?
I've got a pretty good
profile of the killer
figured out, and that guy in
the pictures on her phone
isn't anywhere close, see?
Wha‐‐? A profile?
If it straight up says
‐‐he's a murderer...
‐‐What's this?
It's his mystery‐solving
rakugo deal.
I can't say it's great theatre.
Forensic rakugo?
[SHERLOCK] Hmph. Well,
one thing we do know
is she went into a room
with a total stranger and got
naked right out the gate.
I'd like to meet
a girl like that!
I'm sure you could,
but bring your wallet,
because she won't be
doing it just for fun.
Professionals generally want
to be paid for their work.
[gasps]
Wait, that hostess...
You think the killer works
at the White Rose?
Yeah. Matter of fact,
I'm quite sure of it.
So then, what were you saying
about the killer's profile?
[sighs]
Let's see...
Over a hundred and
eighty centimeters tall.
Might look like
a high roller at a glance,
but actually living
on a pauper's wages.
Likes to unwind with
an occasional cigar.
And the nail on
the right index finger
is a bit longer than the rest.
That about does it.
What makes you
think that they're
over 180 centimeters?
If you look at the spacing
between the footsteps
left on the floor,
it's not hard to tell.
Fair enough.
But where did you get that they
don't make a lot of money?
They had a cigar,
but it wasn't a good one.
Smoked it all the way
down to a stub.
Dumped the ashes
right on the floor.
Nothing but affectation.
A peasant's pretension
to the high life.
And you said
that the killer's
right index
fingernail was long?
Remember those
wings drawn in blood?
On the bits they
would have painted
using their
right index finger,
you could make out a bunch
of scratch marks.
Which means
this one wasn't Jack.
Wait, how can you tell?
'Cause at the
other crime scenes,
Jack always had plenty
of paint to work with.
This time the killer didn't set
about drawing the wings
until the victim's blood
had stopped pumping,
so the palette was a bit dry.
As a result, they had
to spread the blood thin.
Thin enough that that fingernail
scraped right through it.
[doorbell rings]
It seems they've arrived.
When you say "they"...
[SHERLOCK]
Yes, I mean our culprit.
[gasps]
[doorbell ringing]
[doorbell ringing quickly]
I'm here!
Well, that guy
didn't fit the profile‐‐
[grunts]
You kiddin' me?!
You call me out here just to
slam the door in my face?!
Huh?!
Dunno if he killed anyone,
but that jacket's criminal.
This would be Masaya.
Owner of the White Rose.
While he was off in the
back room boffing the girls
who made it past
the job interview‐‐
His personal assistant
would come along
after him looking for scraps.
Uh... That's not. I don't‐‐
Ugh...
You should follow him.
I bet it'll be fun!
See ya later!
Well, why'd you
even call me here?!
Huh?!
[sniffs]
Smell that?
I know that smell!
Yep. Bahamas was right.
[SHERLOCK] Hey, you.
Could I get a light here?
[gasps]
Much obliged, friend.
Hey, old man.
You're tellin' me this
is our guy, right?
[gasps]
[SHERLOCK]
Of course, ya goof.
It's obvious, isn't it?
[ASSISTANT whimpers]
Beg pardon?
[SHERLOCK] When Masaya
rejected a candidate,
this guy would pick her up
and have his way with her.
[SHERLOCK] This time, he called
the victim to that condo,
under the pretext of
a second interview.
[SHERLOCK] He tried
to force himself on her
once she undressed,
but she resisted.
[ASSISTANT]
Calm down. Stop!
[SHERLOCK]
And died for it.
[ASSISTANT gasps]
[gasps]
[SHERLOCK] Our man thought
that he could pin her death
on Jack the Ripper.
[ASSISTANT growls]
[shrieks]
[WATSON gasps]
That's rough.
I guess in the end,
none of it worked out for him.
[WATSON]
Huh?! Come on!
So then, we found
the real killer,
and he turned out
to be a fake Jack.
Do I have that right?
[coughs]
There's a lesson in all this.
How are a fake serial
killer and a fish alike?
Why don'tcha tell us?!
Simple. Neither one
of them wants to get caught.
Thank you all
for joining us today.
Sadly, that's all
the time we have‐‐
[grunts]
[groans]
[WATSON wheezes]
[WATSON]
Mr. Holmes!!!
[SHERLOCK grunts]
[SHERLOCK]
Oh, no...
[HUDSON] We'd be happy to let
you use this room for a while.
I'm in your debt,
and if you need anything done
around the place‐‐
[HUDSON]
Oh?
[WATSON]
I'll help you out any way I can.
[HUDSON] You did say that
you were a doctor, didn't you?
Yes. I am a doctor.
Well then,
isn't this my lucky day.
Body. Move, damn you!
‐‐[knocking]
‐‐[gasps]
No. No, no, stay away.
Don't come in!
[SHERLOCK]
Don't come into my room!
[VOICE]
Sherlock Holmes?
[SHERLOCK]
Cobra?
[VOICE]
Heh. And goodbye.