[LUCY]
Dang it, Mary, c'mon!
Eh‐heh! Sorry, Lucy!
Ugh. Guess I can
let it go this once.
[gasps]
You're the best, Sis!
[chuckles]
[LUCY]
Mm! Good stuff, Mary!
Aw, thanks, glad ya like it!
I feel kinda bad
that I'm always leavin'
the cooking up to you.
Well, ya shouldn't‐‐
it's no bother.
[MARY] Lucy. D'ya think Daddy's
ever gonna come home again?
Either way, ya still have me!
[gasps]
That's right!
[ADOPTIVE MOM]
Let's go, now.
[ADOPTIVE DAD]
Everything's going to be okay.
[MARY] Wait. I don't
wanna leave her behind!
I wanna stay with my big sister!
Lucy. Lucy!
Mary, hold on!
Come on!
Let's both get outta town.
It's you and me, Mary!
I'm always gonna keep you safe!
[gasps]
Yeah!
[LUCY] Kabukicho.
Even if they come lookin',
no way they'll ever
find us around here.
[MARY] From now on, it's gonna
be just the two of us,
right, Lu?
‐‐[LUCY gasps]
‐‐[MARY] Hmm?
[LUCY] On the dark
streets of Kabukicho,
where the trumpeting of
elephants rings in the hour
and villains lurk in every
shadow, six detectives roam.
Freaks, geeks, losers,
and loons to a one.
Where they roam,
chaos will surely follow.
And now they've got
another riddle to solve.
Well, you know the drill, so
just sit back and watch them go.
[HUDSON moans]
Oh...
Oh, is this dress not divine?!
Huh. I guess, but where
would you even wear it?
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
‐‐[MASAYA] Guess who's back!
The legend returns. Huh!
[MASAYA]
You all don't wanna miss it!
Huh!
Little girl,
if I walked in the door
of that host club
wearing this dress,
you'd feel a breeze when
all the heads turned.
‐‐[giggles]
‐‐Uh...
[HUDSON] Oh! It's giving me
chills just thinking about it!
[MARY gasps]
[KOBAYASHI groans]
The Missus sure asks
a lot of people sometimes,
doesn't she?
I'm okay with that.
[PIPE meows]
You, too, Pipe?
You feeling all fresh and clean?
‐‐[WOMAN 5A shrieks]
‐‐[KOBAYASHI gasps]
What was that?
[LUCY bellows]
[THUG 5A groans]
[LUCY yells]
‐‐[THUGS whimpering]
‐‐[THUG 5A] We're sorry!
Thanks so much for your help.
Is there anything
I can do to repay you?
No thanks needed.
I'm glad to help.
Hah! I'll never forget this!
Phoo! Get it, Lady Lu!
Uh‐‐ Huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm...?
[KOBAYASHI panting]
[BOTH gasp]
[SUMOS grunting]
[LUCY]
Uh... Excuse me.
Sorry, but I'm a huge fan.
I... I made these
for you myself, so‐‐
[chuckles]
[BOTH yell]
[KOBAYASHI] So our little
Lu's got herself a crush...
...on a sumo wrestler.
[WATSON] I don't think
I had any idea that there was
a sumo stable there until today.
[KOBAYASHI] Yeah,
it's called the Kuromi Stable.
I've heard a little bit
about 'em, but honestly,
none of it has been good.
That so.
Apparently, this one goes
by the name "Omiyama."
Really? It's been quite a while
since I've heard that name.
As I recall, he was expected
to become a yokozuna
when he was younger.
[MICHEL]
Phoo.
At one time, but that's
ancient history.
He had a bad knee injury
and was never the same again.
He barely even wrestled
in the last tournament.
Hmm.
[WATSON]
So he's over the hill now.
[HUDSON]
He may not win much anymore,
but according to all their
neighbors, he's the only man
out of the whole Kuromi
Stable with a decent heart.
That's all fine and good.
I'd say it's more his brain
that's the problem, though.
Seriously, what a boring
way to end a career.
Uh?
[MICHEL] If he loses
this next tournament,
he gets knocked
down to makushita. Huh.
Considering his age, that might
be enough to push him to retire.
I bet that's why
Lady Lu is so gung‐ho
about supporting the guy.
Why is it so hard to save money?
Lucy. I have to go
to this cram school!
Wait, two million yen
and you need it in two days?
If I don't get into cram school,
there's no way I'll
ever be able to live
the glamorous college life
that I've always dreamed about!
But we just don't have
that kind of money, Mary.
[MARY]
Hmm.
Yeah, that's fair‐‐
it is expensive.
[LUCY groans]
Don't worry about it.
Forget that I
even brought it up‐‐
[LUCY]
Let's do it.
One way or another,
I'm gonna get that money.
Ah. You mean it?
You bet. So you
focus on studying
and let me take care
of this stuff, okay?
In fact, you can leave all the
housekeeping and laundry to me.
No distractions.
Hah! Thanks so much!
‐‐Know what?
‐‐Ah?
[LUCY] I think I might even
take over cooking duty‐‐
[MARY]
You absolutely will not.
The kitchen is my turf,
no exceptions. Got it?
Right. I got it.
[KANEKO]
Why, certainly.
I would be happy to
lend you the money.
[LUCY] Thank you, Boss
Kaneko. It means a lot.
You have two weeks.
If the loan's not repaid
in full by that time,
then you're going to have
to work off the balance.
I'm sure I can find an
opening in one of my clubs.
Ah. What kind of clubs...?
[sleazy trumpet playing]
[WOMAN moaning]
[LUCY gulps]
Understood, sir.
I'll have all of the money
back to you in two weeks.
[sighs]
Moriarty?
I didn't expect to run into
him in this part of town.
[MORIARTY]
Ah. Hey there, Lucy!
[LUCY] Looks like you've
got a lot in that bag.
Ah! I'm taking a pretty
long trip to a friend's place
for summer vacation.
[MORIARTY] Whoa, that guy's
sitting there staring over
the edge and looking
contemplative.
You think maybe he's gonna jump?
[gasps]
Not if we stop him. Come on!
Don't do it!
[BUNMARU yells]
Please let go of me!
I'm not gonna let you jump!
A little help, here?!
R‐Right!
[LUCY, MORIARTY]
One, two!
[BUNMARU yells]
‐‐[MORIARTY yelps]
‐‐Hey, wait. Don't I know you?
‐‐Get off me already!
‐‐My entire body...
...falling asleep!
[LUCY]
Here you go.
[BUNMARU]
Thank you very much, miss.
So, who is this? You know him?
Not really. We just
ran into each other recently.
That's right.
My name is Bunmaru,
a wrestler from the
Kuromi sumo stable,
and Omiyama's attendant.
Huh. What were
you doing up here?
I mean, other than scaring Lucy.
[BUNMARU]
That's a long story.
You see, our building hasn't
been in the best shape
for awhile now, and
we recently decided it was
finally time to make
some long‐needed repairs.
[LUCY]
Yeah, makes sense.
That building is just
about falling apart. Go on.
Well, last night...
...I was given two million yen
collected by our supporters
to put toward
renovating the stable.
But then I got drunk and
now all the money is gone!
Two million yen?
That's not good.
Maybe we shouldn't
have interrupted you.
[BUNMARU] The contractors
are asking for the money
by noon today,
and the only way I can pay
this debt is with my life,
so please don't interfere!
[LUCY]
That's not gonna help!
If you kill yourself it'll only
make things worse for Omiyama,
so knock it off!
But there's no way
I can ever show my face
at the stable again!
‐‐[LUCY growls]
‐‐[BUNMARU] Uh?
What's this? Where
did you get all this money?
It's yours.
[BUNMARU] That's very
generous, but I can't accept.
Y'already did. Take it and go.
Ah... Ah! I shall be
forever in your debt, miss!
[panting]
Why did I do that?!
Forgive me, Mary!
[MORIARTY]
Mary? I get it.
So what expensive thing
is she asking for now?
I think your life would be
a lot easier if you could
learn to tell her no.
Yeah. I know that she
can be selfish sometimes,
and that I shouldn't give in...
...but she's my sister,
the only one I've got.
[MORIARTY grunts]
[LUCY]
You understand, don't you?
Since you've got a sister, too.
Yeah, I get it.
That's why... I'll make it work,
one way or another!
[KANEKO] Certainly,
another two million yen.
But I would like to
make it perfectly clear to you
that your due date
remains the same.
Do you accept those terms?
I can make that work.
Four million in two weeks!
I'll pay you back,
whatever it takes!
[MARY sighs, yawns]
Crap. I didn't mean to sleep in.
[gasps]
Oh, Lucy!
[HUDSON] You're looking for
any work you can get, you say?
I've got A‐rank jobs piling up,
you're more than welcome
to pull some off the stack.
Can I really? Thank you!
[OMIYAMA]
Pardon me.
I'm looking for Lucy Morstan,
and I was told that
I could find her here.
[LUCY]
Huh?!
We're very grateful
for your help, young lady.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's thanks to you
that we were able to pay
the contractors on time.
[HUDSON]
That's wonderful to hear.
Though I'm still curious how
a man would go about losing
that much cash.
About that...
I went to pick up
the two million yesterday,
and while I was visiting
our supporters' office,
it so happens that
they offered me a drink.
Honestly, I worried about
sending him for that reason.
Bunmaru doesn't hold his liquor
well, and allowing him to drink
often ends with him
unconscious in the street.
That is the sad truth.
Anyway...
I certainly had
no intention of getting
drunk there, but nonetheless,
on my way back to the stable,
I found myself suddenly
getting very sleepy.
[BUNMARU snoring]
[BUNMARU]
Huh...?
It's gone!
[BUNMARU]
And when I finally woke up,
I found the money
had all disappeared.
[BUNMARU]
It's all gone!
Which is the point in
the story where you came in.
[HUDSON] And have you gone
to the police about this?
Oh, no...
I didn't want this to
affect Bunmaru's future.
For his sake, we're handling
this matter discretely.
Of course, I'll return
the two million yen
as soon as I'm able.
[OMIYAMA] He's my attendant,
and his failure
is my responsibility.
You haven't changed a bit.
Please, sir. There's
no need for you to worry.
I just remembered!
The food you brought for us
that day was wonderful.
I could hardly keep
myself away from it!
[LUCY]
Was it really?
That's a better response
than I usually get.
Yes, I was amazed that you
were able to make it yourself.
It was perfectly chewy, like you
would find at the store‐‐
Bunmaru! This is hardly
the time to gush over food!
I'm so sorry!
I think he just
gave away the game.
Kuma, I need you to go
pick something up.
Sure thing!
Pick up some what?
[OMIYAMA] Right, then.
We'd best be on our way.
Sir! I'm gonna be rooting for
you in the next tournament!
Give it everything you've got!
Your excitement is heartwarming.
Now what was it you were telling
me about needing to earn money?
Oh, right!
Whatever job you can
give me, I'll take it.
I want everything you've got,
no matter how small it may be!
Yes, who's there?
Ah. Could it be...?
[LUCY]
One million nine‐seventy.
One million nine‐eighty,
one million nine‐ninety...
That's two million.
[phone alarm beeping]
Ugh.
Hey there. It's been
a while, hasn't it, Doctor?
Boss Kaneko!
Thank you for all your
help on the West Side, sir.
I was able to make
my way to Kabukicho.
And you're adjusting
to the place okay?
Yeah, though
Mister Holmes still hasn't
heard about my case.
I'm not surprised.
His two joys in life are rakugo
and making people
jump through hoops.
I don't envy
the position you're in.
Maybe so.
He's definitely been
keeping me busy.
But still... I dunno.
Somehow, I can't bring
myself to hate the guy.
Well, h e's very good
at what he does,
so bear with it, my friend.
Right. Thank you
for everything, sir.
While we're here,
how has Little Lu been doing?
[LUCY]
Get your hands off me right now!
[WATSON]
Just come here!
Mister Holmes, I know that
you've figured this out.
And you've got more than
enough money to take care
of what she owes!
Get off me!
This isn't your problem!
I'm not going to let this go.
You need two million more yen
by the end of the day!
So why don't you
go get your money back?
[BOTH grunt]
[SHERLOCK] Just find the person
who stole the two million off
that bumbling sumo boy.
I'm sure it hasn't
been spent yet.
[LUCY gasps]
[WATSON]
You know who the thief is?
Obviously. Wanna hear?
Of course! Tell us!
[chuckles]
So, old man.
Did you really figure out
who took all that money
from Bunmaru?
Yeah.
But before I explain, you should
try one of those daifuku
you picked up the other day.
[gasps]
Sure, it's pretty good.
What's that got to do
with the money?
It is good.
Bunmaru was raving
about it, wasn't he?
[LUCY gasps]
[LUCY]
Omiyama!
I challenge you to a match!
[LUCY] Let her go!
Get away from my sister!
[THUG 5B]
Back off, you little brat!
Lucy, no!
Come with me.
Keep your mouth shut.
[OMIYAMA] Where do you think
you're going with that child?
Huh? Oof!
[THUG 5A]
We... We'll never do it again!
[THUG 5B yells]
[OMIYAMA] You were protecting
your little sister.
That's commendable.
This town is a hard place
for good people to live.
Be strong.
Stay on the high road.
I will!
Omiyama!
[gruntin]
What are you trying to do?
Ah! Miss Lucy? Please.
Are you upset about something?
[LUCY grunts]
I've admired you since
the day I came to Kabukicho.
You were the one who told me
I should stay on the high road!
Yeah, thanks,
but I think I'm good.
I always thought daifuku tasted
better without the drugs.
[WATSON]
What do you mean without‐‐?!
[grunts, coughs]
They were a pain
in the ass to get, though.
'Cause that particular drug has
been in high demand recently.
All the kids are crazy about
the "delayed onset" thing.
But wait...
Didn't Lucy bring the ones
that Bunmaru ate?
If she made 'em herself,
I think she'd probably
leave the drugs out.
Bunmaru said the daifuku
he had were excellent.
No way Lucy made them.
[BOTH gasp]
If Mary Morstan is willing
to actually pick up
a knife to get out of eating it.
Lucy's cooking must be rank.
And that means...
The food Lucy brought to the
stable and the food Bunmaru ate
weren't the same.
Okay.
But how do you figure it was the
daifuku that put him to sleep?
Bunmaru said he took
it easy on the booze,
and yet he still started getting
sleepy as he was walking home.
And it takes a professional
to make a mochi with
that chewy texture.
So I did some
research and confirmed
with the man himself
that the brand you bought
was what he'd eaten.
Lemme get this straight.
The criminal drugged Bunmaru
with sedative‐laced daifuku,
and then stole the cash
off him once he passed out.
Wait, then did Lucy do it?!
Ugh... You moron.
Were you paying attention?
We just established that
the culprit swapped
Lucy's daifuku for these.
That was... literally
that whole conversation.
Well... then who did
the dirty daifuku deed?
[OMIYAMA]
I'm sorry...
[SHERLOCK] The culprit was
none other than Omiyama.
It's true.
I set Bunmaru up
and took the money.
[OMIYAMA] I put the drugged
daifuku out where he was sure
to see them, with a note saying
that a fan had brought them.
I knew Bunmaru loved daifuku,
and there was no way
he'd pass them up.
After that, all I had
to do was follow him
until he collected the money.
Then once the
sedatives kicked in,
I stole it off of him.
I needed that money,
to rig my next match!
No... You wouldn't, would you?
Yes.
I barely wrestled in
my last tournament.
And I thought if I was demoted.
I would never be able to claw
my way back up from makushta.
Then they offered
to fix my match!
In the end, the big guy
caved to temptation, huh?
The truth is, this kind
of match fixing happens
all the time in sumo.
Gamblers get a payday and
wrestlers stay in the game.
[gasps]
What a boring way
to end a career like his.
So, what does fixing a
sumo match have in common
with eating homemade snacks that
a fan gave you as a present?
Why don't you tell us?
It can leave a bad
taste in your mouth.
[SHERLOCK] That's all
the time we have for today.
[WATSON]
Question.
How do you know Omiyama
still has the money?
Couldn't he have spent
some of it already?
[SHERLOCK]
Hmm! That one's simple enough.
[WATSON]
I see.
He lost every match
in the tournament,
which means he didn't buy a win.
I've been eliminated from
the tournament as of today.
After all this, I even managed
to fail in my effort to cheat.
Miss Lucy. Bunmaru.
I sincerely apologize.
So please, take your money.
[LUCY]
Ah.
[BUNMARU sobbing]
Omiyama!
Yeah, you're still
the man you were.
‐‐[LUCY] It's yours.
‐‐Wha‐‐ I couldn't possibly!
[LUCY] Sure you can.
Call it a parting gift.
And stay on the high
road from now on.
Can you believe that
somebody had the nerve
to go and buy my dress?
Jesus, I look like the first one
kicked out of the chorus line.
No! You're a vision!
Hiya!
[MORIARTY]
Hey, Mary!
How did Lucy's
whole thing turn out?
[HUDSON]
Good question.
As I recall, that four million
yen was due today, wasn't it?
Wait, what are
you guys talking about?
[panting]
[MARY]
Sis. What do I do now?!
This isn't what I wanted!
I'm so sorry!
Where's Lucy?!
[KANEKO] You look well,
Mary, but I'm afraid
you just missed her.
She's heading to the club now.
[MARY] No! It should
be me working there!
Let me take her place!
I'll pay back whatever
she owes. So please!
[KANEKO] Dear, you're hardly
suited for the kind of work
I have your sister doing.
And why not?!
Here's a fresh face for you.
Let's give it up
for our new boy, Lou!
‐‐Hey, ladies.
‐‐[WOMEN screaming]
[MASAYA] I won't say
he's not a snack, girls,
but let's not forget
tonight's main course.
i.e. me, the legendary
host, Masaya! Huh!
And I wanna thank you all
for coming out to my party‐‐
[DIANA, CHINKILL, MAKI]
Lu‐Lu, we came to see you!
[LUCY grunts]
Easy! You're gonna rip the suit!
What's he got that
I don't got? Huh...
[MARY]
Hey, everybody!
Make sure you all spend plenty
of money on my boy Lou!
Wait, Mary! The hell?!
Tsk. How boring is that?
This says Bunmaru
moved up to juryo.
Huh.
Sounds like he was
a pretty good wrestler
in his own right.
And since he moved up,
Omiyama dropped
two million yen on an apron
for his ring entrances.
[gasps] That's right.
The case I mentioned before.
It actually started when the
victim ate a mitarashi dango
and‐‐ And I... I guess...
...I'll... tell you later....
[snores]
So it takes three hours
for effect to kick in.
Just as advertised.
[CLUB PATRONS murmuring]
[MARY] Aw! Damn, I am cute!
Good eye, Mrs. Hudson!
Mary! Don't tell me
you spent your tuition
on a stupid dress!
[MARY giggles]
Sorry, Lucy.
[SUGIMOTO] Lift your fists into
the sky, cry if ya want.
A tabby try'na live
a tiger life, though.