[MYCROFT] Then you're granting
me full discretion to act,
Ward Mayor Moran?
That's correct.
You're to return this item
to me, whatever it takes.
[MYCROFT]
Understood, sir.
Do you have any leads as
to who may have taken it?
She's the culprit?
The woman's brilliant,
beautiful, and cunning
as a snake,
but with half the charm
and not a bit of the warmth.
Irene Adler is our thief.
[WATSON sighs] I'm glad we
could find your trading cards.
Though the one‐per‐customer
limit did throw me a little bit.
What's the deal there?
Are those things really
that hard to get?
[SHERLOCK]
Yeah.
This whole line of cards
has gone out of print.
And after I've found
Master Koyoru's card,
I'll have a complete set!
[giggles]
[WATSON]
Oh, hey. Mr. Kobayashi!
Ah? Ha! Didn't think I'd
be seeing you two at this hour!
There was an early
bird sale this morning.
[SHERLOCK] So what are all these
people standing around for?
For the latest A.I!
The day has finally come!
It's time to unveil mankind's
bridge into the future.
Allow me to introduce you
to the newest generation
of the Real Wife:
Airi, version 6.9!
[CROWD cheers]
Don't be shy, honey.
Go on and introduce yourself
to the whole world.
I love you, darling.
‐‐[CROWD] Yeah!
‐‐[GODFREY] Today is the future!
[CROWD]
Future!
[KOBAYASHI]
You guys are out of the loop.
She's A.I, or Airi for short,
and she's so totally perfect
that every new version sells out
immediately on launch day!
[WATSON, KOBAYASHI]
Uh?
[SHERLOCK]
You'll need these.
You're the best,
Sherlock, thanks!
[giggles]
[SHERLOCK]
Koyoru, Koyoru, Koyoru, Koyoru.
Come on, Koyoru!
Tss! Aww...
What would he want with
all those tissues you gave him?
Come on. Give me Koyoru!
Koyoru. Koyoru. Koyoru.
[gasps]
[SHERLOCK]
Ahh‐‐!
[whimpers]
[WATSON groans]
[WATSON] Seriously, what's
he going to be wiping up?
[SHERLOCK]
Seriously. Google it, ya virgin.
Ah! That's rude,
and way off base.
Ah.
Been waiting for you, boys.
[HUDSON] This is the
biggest one in a while,
so I'm expecting
everyone to want in.
[WATSON] Ah, so that
does happen sometimes.
Though I think Mr. Kobayashi
is still in line.
[MYCROFT] Then we're going
to have to start without him.
[SHERLOCK gasps]
Pass on this one.
[MYCROFT] Surely you
can hear me out at least.
Isn't that fair, little brother?
[gasping]
[growls]
[SHERLOCK]
Mycroft...
[MYCROFT]
Hmm.
[MYCROFT] Here on the dark
streets of Kabukicho,
where the trumpeting of
elephants rings in the hour
and evil lurks in every
shadow, six detectives roam.
Freaks, geeks, losers,
and loons to a one.
Where they roam,
chaos will surely follow.
And you fine people
are invited to watch
their wild war of
wills and wits.
Brothers, huh?
Yes, that's correct.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Mycroft.
I'm Sherlock's older brother.
[FUYUTO] To think
that such an important man
could share genes
with that weirdo.
‐‐[MYCROFT] Who are you?
‐‐[FUYUTO] I'm Kyogoku Fuyuto...
So he's a big deal?
Ah. Yeah. He says
he's Ward Mayor Moran's
top secretary.
By the way, here's something
to sweeten the pot.
[gasping]
So what is that, and why
am I supposed to care?
Apologies. Just a small extra.
[SHERLOCK whimpers]
[MYCROFT chuckles]
This is an S Rank with bonus,
and you're looking at a
payout of 15,000,000 yen
plus the trading card.
[gasping]
Well, Mikey‐dear.
Why don't you fill us in?
[MYCROFT]
Right, then.
I'm hiring you all
to retrieve a stolen item.
Namely, a USB memory stick
belonging to Mayor Moran,
which looks like this.
[FUYUTO]
A fried egg?
[MARY]
Are you serious right now?
Who would buy that?
It disappeared two weeks ago.
It would seem that someone
stole the mayor's USB stick
while he was asleep.
Shortly thereafter,
the mayor received an email
from the culprit threatening
to publish its contents
unless he paid an
exorbitantly high ransom.
The blackmailer
is this woman, Irene Adler.
[MARY]
I know her.
She's been a commentator
on TV before, right?
She's a renowned expert
in both education and finance.
A violin virtuoso, too.
A true renaissance woman
with endless talent and drive!
And how do you know
this woman is our thief?
Access, for one thing.
She previously worked in
the Moran family's employ
as a private tutor.
Huh...
Of course, and I'm
sure that an affair
was involved as well right?
What's on the drive anyway?
[MYCROFT] Something that
can't be allowed to get out.
That's as much as I can say.
We're keeping this away
from the police for a reason.
So a past relationship
and a drive full of secret data.
From what you've told us,
revenge porn sounds
like a safe bet.
[MYCROFT sighs]
As has been mentioned,
this woman is
also quite brilliant.
We've consulted with numerous
detectives and even criminals,
and she's made a fool
of each one to date.
[gasps]
[MYCROFT]
Hmm.
[SHERLOCK] Hmph. Give her what
she wants and be done with it.
Three hundred million
yen is a lot of money.
‐‐[gasping]
‐‐[MICHEL] Wow.
And assuming
we can produce that sum,
it still doesn't guarantee that
she would return the drive.
What's more, she could
easily have duplicated the data
by this point, couldn't she?
Fortunately,
that's not a concern.
The files on this drive
are impossible to copy.
One more
important point to note.
Miss Adler will be moving out of
her house a few days from now.
So do be aware that
you'll be working under
a tight deadline on this case.
I take it that's
all for the explanation.
Ugh...
What's going on?
The Missus seems
kind of down today.
[LUCY] Hmm. She does,
now that you mention it.
[HUDSON]
Hmm.
[sighs]
I leave it to you,
my dearest little brother.
[SHERLOCK]
Ugh.
You seem interested, Doctor.
Feel free to take my place.
Ah! Hold on. Why me?
Just go.
After the sun has set
upon all the rest of the world,
our little town of Kabukicho
blah, blah‐bblah, blah‐blah.
If gold and silver
are what you're after,
then track down the mayor's
dick pic memory stick.
A light gleams
in these detectives' eyes.
This is a haven for
outcasts and oddballs,
and you're the reason they call
it "the Detectives' Row House."
Fifteen million yen
to whoever is able to secure
Mayor Moran's USB key drive.
[pop]
It should be somewhere close.
[MARY grunts]
Hey!
[LUCY] C'mon, we didn't
even do anything!
Watch the hands, creep!
[LUCY growls]
[police siren wails]
That must be the place.
‐‐[OLD MAN groans]
‐‐[MAID 7A] Ahh!
Oh, no! Hold on, sir, I'll
call a doctor right away!
[gasps]
What's wrong?
[MAID 7A] He was walking along
and suddenly collapsed!
[WATSON] Stay with me,
sir, it'll be okay.
Are you in any pain?
Ah. Ah!
Please, calm down, sir.
I'm a doctor, I can help.
[IRENE]
What's going on here?
[OLD MAN] I suffer from acute
compartment syndrome, miss.
May I please rest inside while
I wait for an ambulance?
Wait. Compartment syndrome's
making you spit blood?
[IRENE]
Hmm. Johnny. Hakamada.
You're an absolute
embarrassment.
‐‐[GUARD 7A] Come on, get up.
‐‐[FUYUTO] I regret everything!
[GUARD 7A]
Walk!
Bring him inside.
The doctor here will
be needing a new shirt.
‐‐Huh...? Ah!
‐‐Yes, understood, ma'am.
Follow me, please.
[WATSON]
Of course. Thank you, miss!
Pink, huh? Nice.
[LEAD MOVER]
Beg your pardon, ma'am.
[MOVERS]
Excuse us!
Sorry, but we have
to pat you down.
[LEAD MOVER] Will we be
packing everything for you?
We can take care
of whatever you need.
[IRENE] Don't touch anything
in the back room upstairs,
I'll deal with that myself.
But go ahead and pack the rest.
[LEAD MOVER]
Understood.
The back room upstairs, huh?
It's locked.
[GODFREY]
This way.
Yes, I'm going to be departing
for New York City tomorrow.
Uh! U‐Um, hi.
Ah, you must be the doctor!
I was hoping that I might
run into you here.
Yes, sir.
Ah. And you're the one
who makes those dolls!
Then you're familiar
with my Real Wives?
Godfrey Norton. It's a pleasure.
And I'm John Wa‐‐
Kobayashi, sir.
[GODFREY]
Hmm...
Heh, heh...
Doctor Kobayashi Johnwa.
May I ask you to lend me
your expertise for a bit?
[gasps]
[WATSON] Hmm. You might consider
offering multiple options
for thickness and
elasticity of skin.
Maybe a range of resting
body temperatures?
Excellent thoughts!
Only a true professional
could hold such insights
‐‐into the human body!
‐‐[WATSON] One thing here.
This seems just a bit off to me.
[GODFREY]
Fantastic!
Now that you mention it,
it does, doesn't it?
[laughs]
You're a sharp one.
I think I need to get your eyes
on my unannounced line
of new ladies!
[WATSON]
Hmm?
[AIRI]
I love you.
Ti amo.
[GODFREY] The Real Wife
is going international.
And tomorrow, these Airi World
Models begin their journeys
across the globe!
It's my great undertaking:
to offer my Airi, the perfect
wife, to men of every nation.
[WATSON] Is your real, er,
your actual wife going?
Yes. But for the moment,
I'll be leaving her to
take care of our new house.
And I'll be taking
the Airis here‐‐
[IRENE]
Dear? There you are.
What are you doing?
[GODFREY]
Hello, honey! Heh.
I was asking our new friend
Johnwa for his opinions
on the World Models.
[IRENE] You were also showing
off an unannounced project
‐‐to the movers, dear.
‐‐[GODFREY] Ah!
I suppose I was. My apologies.
Let's get you to work
taking care of the trash.
Follow me.
[IRENE chuckles]
Ma'am. Will you need us
to pack this room?
[IRENE]
No, thanks.
These are Godfrey's babies
and he's terribly protective.
He told me that he would
prefer to pack and load
each one personally.
[LEAD MOVER]
Understood. Well, then.
Sorry for taking up
so much of your time.
No. Mr. Norton
seems like a great husband.
He's not my husband yet.
Ah. I wasn't aware!
‐‐[crashing]
‐‐[BOTH] Ah.
[IRENE sighs]
[pager meowing, buzzing]
Wait, what French girl?
[gasps]
[AIRI]
Je t'aime.
[speaking French]
Today is the future!
[AIRI]
Voulez‐vous coucher avec moi?
[WATSON gasps]
[SHERLOCK] Get in the truck,
Doctor Johnwa Kobayashi.
[WATSON]
Sherlock!
Guess I'm not as useless
as you thought, am I?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Fortunately, Kyogoku
is staggeringly incompetent.
How did you know?
Ah...
You bugged me?!
So that's why
you had me go ahead.
But how did you get a mover's
uniform and a van?
[SHERLOCK]
That was the easiest part.
I just handed a wad of bills
to the movers' boss.
It was nothing next to the
card‐‐ Uh, cold hard cash
I'll be getting
out of this case.
[WATSON]
That Irene was gorgeous, though.
[SHERLOCK]
Was she?
[WATSON] How did you know where
that USB drive was, anyway?
[SHERLOCK] Tch. Clearly,
Doctor Johnwa Kobayashi
is no detective.
Let that go already!
[yawns]
[FUYUTO] Ugh! Irene. I swear I'm
coming for that drive tomorrow!
You wish!
Not if I get to it first, kid.
Wanna make a bet?
Oh, please, you still
haven't even met the woman!
[laughter]
[FUYUTO growls]
They're so obnoxious.
Anyway, wanna, like, sneak off?
[MAKI]
Mm?
[FUYUTO gasps]
[SHERLOCK]
Hmm. Hmm!
Are you practicing your
goofy‐looking faces?
Why would I practice?
I'm deducting.
Obviously the USA‐whatever
thing has to be
in the bedroom, doesn't it?
Ugh. Good job.
Now can you narrow it down?
There are lots of hiding
spots in a bedroom.
Yep! and it's definitely
in one of 'em!
That's as far as you got?
Sorry to tell you, but you
haven't deduced anything.
Although, I didn't have
to deduce anything
either this time.
She told me herself
where to find it.
‐‐Huh?!
‐‐It's simple.
When I asked if she wanted the
movers to pack up that room,
she said to leave it, and
that Godfrey intended
to pack up all the Airis
and load them individually.
Seems like a strange answer.
Were they the
only things in that room
that needed to be moved?
Nah, there was
furniture and paintings
‐‐and all kinds of stuff!
‐‐Right.
But she responded like
I asked her specifically
about packing the dolls.
She was so focused
on where she hid that drive
that she answered
the wrong question.
Oh, hey, you're right!
But that guy had a robo‐wife
for every day of the week!
And anyone could
have had the whatsit,
so how'd you figure
it was the French girl?
That's the easiest
question you've asked yet.
Each doll was going
to be shipped out
to a different country,
with the husband following along
after them, but that
doesn't quite explain
how the wife fit
into the whole plan.
I thought he said
that she was gonna be
‐‐moving into their new house.
‐‐He did mention that.
Meaning whichever one
of those dolls was going
to the same country as
she was, would be the one
hiding the drive.
Oh, right! And the tag
on the wife's suitcase
said it was headed
for somewhere in France!
So, then, nothing
left to do but plug it in
and see what's inside.
But I figure there's probably
going to be a password.
Only one way to find out!
There's a lesson in this.
What does a secret thumb drive
holding all your homemade porn
have in common
with an ultra‐rare
out‐of‐print
trading card?
Why don't ya tell us?!
You don't want
someone else getting it.
And that's all
our time for today.
[WATSON]
Sherlock?
[SHERLOCK]
Ah... A‐Ah...
[growls]
‐‐Damn her!
‐‐[WATSON] A‐Ah! Wait a minute.
Sherlock, what's the matter?
Hey, where are you going?!
[sighs]
Hold on. What is this?
She was onto us the whole time?
[WATSON]
Sherlock!
We never had her fooled.
Irene knew everything
from the start!
Yeah. That was not the drive
we were looking for.
‐‐This is a nice little place.
‐‐I swear that woman's a witch!
My bad!
[DRUNK 7B guffaws] Kinda early
in the night for that!
[DRUNK 7A chuckles]
I can rally.
[snarls]
Eh? What's up?
[IRENE] It's lovely to see you
again, Mister Sherlock Holmes.
[SHERLOCK]
What are you doing here?
[IRENE] I just wanted to say
hello to an old friend.
[SHERLOCK grunts]
Ugh. You two are
ruining the ambience.
This is exactly why
I didn't want this case.
[IRENE] Ah. Good evening
to you too, Doctor Watson.
Wait. Is it
Doctor Kobayashi now?
Or Johnwa?
[WATSON chuckles]
Oh, dear,
that's quite the scowl.
[giggles]
I'm sorry to tell you all, but
the real flash drive has already
made its way to
Paris ahead of me.
And with that...
...I'll be going.
I'll drop in again if
I should find myself in Japan.
Au revoir.
Hey, Sherlock?
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐Ah!
[WATSON]
Ahh...
[DRUNK 7C groans]
Your money or your life, pal!
Please don't hurt me...
‐‐Get lost!
‐‐Sorry, have you seen Sherlock?
[SABURO]
Yeah, he was goin' that‐a‐way.
‐‐Thanks!
‐‐Hey!
Where is the drive...?
Tell me...
[IRENE]
Ah!
[SHERLOCK]
Back off!
‐‐[MYSTERY MAN 7A growls]
‐‐Ah!
[WATSON]
Huh?!
[gasps]
You needed to hide
that data badly enough
that you'd make a dummy drive.
A woman as cautious as you
would never part with
something that important.
Not even for a second.
I appreciate that you were
still kind enough
to tell me where it was.
Hmph.
[MORIARTY]
Sherlock did that?
[SABURO]
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever
seen him look that mad.
[MORIARTY]
Aw...
A new face. Who is he?
Never seen him.
Could be a new client, I guess.
[SHERLOCK]
Looks like this was a bust.
[MYCROFT]
Maybe not.
We might be able
to restore the data.
If we're able to
authenticate the drive,
we'll be happy to pay in full.
In any case, you're still the
best at what you do, Sherlock.
[MYCROFT] That's done.
No reason for me to linger here.
Great. Thanks for the business.
[KOBAYASHI whimpers]
So. What's this guy's deal?
[whimpering continues]
[HUDSON]
He's got a rash.
[SHERLOCK]
Now that's unfortunate.
And Norton took
the money and ran.
[whines]
My junk is on fire!
There. You should be fine.
Thanks, Doctor.
You can thank her lover
for that rash, Watson.
Assuming you're able
to find him, of course.
Huh? What are
you talking about?
Give me back my USB drive.
It's too late for that.
Sherlock already gave it
back to Mycroft, didn't you?
[WATSON]
Ah! Then the one you passed off
to Mycroft was the fake?
What about the reward?
[SHERLOCK]
Hmph. Hm, hm, hmm...
There's not really
porn on this flash drive,
is there?
[SHERLOCK]
Now, what's the password?
Jugemu Jugemu Goko‐no Surikire
Kaijarisuigyo‐no
Suigyomatsu Unraimatsu
Furaimatsu Ponpokopi!