[SHERLOCK]
Now, what's the password?
You were never trying
to blackmail Moran,
and Mycroft knew it.
You're not interested
in money at all.
What you want is
the contents of the drive.
[gasping]
Nicely done.
Wait. You're saying he's right?
There's no reason
for her to get caught up
in a blackmail scheme.
She would have been swimming
in sex doll money in a few days.
Password.
If I knew it, we wouldn't
be talking right now.
The plan was to get
the drive out of Japan
far beyond Moran's reach.
Why go to all that trouble?
Well. Have fun trying
to crack your egg.
[NEWSCASTER 8A] Six months
later, the question remains.
Where is Jack the Ripper?
Though there have been no
new murders tied to Jack since
the death of
Mayor Moran's daughter,
the killer is still at large,
his true identity unknown.
[MORAN] My highest
priority now is to bring
my daughters...
Now, with the murderer
still on the loose,
the current lull in violence
brings no comfort to
the grieving families
of his victims,
and the people of
Shinjuku can't yet re‐‐
[KOBAYASHI whistling]
[KOBAYASHI grunts]
Sorry, kid.
There's something I was
not expecting to see.
[SHERLOCK]
Hmm?
[PIPE purring]
[WATSON]
Ms. Adler?
[IRENE]
Huh?
[WATSON gasps]
Why are you here?
[IRENE] And what business
is that of yours, exactly?
It's fine! She's lending us
a hand with the bar for a while.
‐‐What for?
‐‐[HUDSON yelps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Well, the Missus has been having
some back pain issues lately.
But this angel‐‐she rented
a room nearby so
she could help out!
Aww, what a sweetheart, right?
Clean the bathrooms.
Please, dear?
[KOBAYASHI]
Right away, ma'am!
[whimpers]
[FUYUTO] Beer taps
are clean, spic and span.
So now that that's done.
Is there somebody you could
talk to about getting me
those papers to
move to the West‐‐
Would you mind cleaning
under the sink, please?
[FUYUTO]
Consider it done!
Ugh. She's trained
you like dogs.
[MORIARTY]
Hi, guys.
Hey. How's it been?
All good.
My! What a handsome boy!
Fun! Just what this place needs!
A middle‐aged woman.
[FUYUTO] Ah! Thanks for
coming through for me!
‐‐Have at.
‐‐Huzzah!
Ah‐ha‐ha!
How long can I keep it?
‐‐Consider it yours, friend.
‐‐Thank you!
[WATSON]
You're already leaving?
[MORIARTY]
Yep.
Hmm?
Huh?
[WATSON]
Mrs. Hudson?
Is your back still hurting?
[HUDSON] Oh, don't
trouble yourself over me.
It's that time of month is all.
I'm fine, darlings, get started.
Oh, my god...
My name is Yui Shirota.
My ex‐husband...
He wants‐‐to steal my daughter.
He's trying to get
full custody of Emiri.
[giggles]
But it's strange.
He‐He didn't want kids.
He left me as soon as
he learned I was pregnant.
I've raised Emiri by myself.
We've never had much, but we've
always been happy together.
[YUI]
Then, last week,
he called me out of nowhere and
told me he wanted to take Emiri.
We never filed for divorce,
so legally, we're still married.
But why now?
[YUI] I don't know.
Of course, I refused.
And then he threatened
to reveal my secret.
Which would be...?
[YUI] I've never had a
very strong constitution.
One time last year,
the stress caught up with me
and I collapsed.
After they treated
me at the hospital,
the doctor told me that my
condition might make it
difficult to raise a child.
But I couldn't imagine giving up
my only daughter for anything.
So I paid him to keep it quiet.
Then I received this
from my ex‐husband.
The medical chart
from my hospital stay.
If I don't give him Emiri,
he'll sue for custody using
my diagnosis as
evidence against me.
[MICHEL] So you're going to
need one of us to track down
your original medical chart.
Yes. I want you
to steal it for me.
So that's the job.
It's an S‐rank with no bonus
and a 1,000,000 reward.
[GROUP grunts]
I've got business
to attend to. Pass on this one.
Hah! Jerkin'
it isn't "business."
So. What can you
tell us about your ex?
His name is Milverton.
Here's a picture.
He used to be a writer
for a weekly paper,
but when I called them,
they said he had retired.
[YUI] One of his former
colleagues told me that
I would probably find him
working somewhere in Kabukicho,
but that's all the information
they had, so I have no idea
‐‐where to start.
‐‐Yeah?
Then you've come to
the right place, miss!
When it comes to
finding people in Kabukicho,
everyone in this row
house is an expert.
[HUDSON] Sure, but I've
never even seen the guy.
What do you think?
I'm out. Not worth it.
Well, I'd like to help.
Ah?
[GROUP]
Hmm?
That's fine. After all, Sherlock
won't be needing his pager.
Augh!
Which means, we're partners now.
Let's get to it,
Johnwa Kobayashi.
‐‐Stop!
‐‐Um... I'm Kobayashi.
[HUDSON] After the sun has set
upon the rest of the world.
Our little town of Kabukicho
lights up in neon.
If gold and silver are
what you're after,
steal back the secret that
would tear this family apart.
A light gleams in these
detectives' eyes.
This is a haven for
outcasts and oddballs.
And you're
the reason they call it
"the Detectives' Row House."
Mwah!
A cool million goes
to the one who finds
Yu‐Yu's medical chart.
Ready...
Go!
[YUI gasps]
‐‐[HUDSON] Are you all right?
‐‐[SHERLOCK] Hmm?
[HUDSON] Hold on, darling,
your face is a bit flushed.
Oh, no! You're burning up!
To the hospital!
Sherlock, hold down
the fort, sweetie!
[SHERLOCK]
Wha‐‐
[EMIRI]
Huh...
[SHERLOCK whimpers]
[stomach growling]
[SHERLOCK groans]
[EMIRI giggle]
‐‐[EMIRI] Ew!
‐‐[SHERLOCK groans]
[WATSON] What are we doing
in a Mahjong parlor?
If the man's in Kabukicho,
and the Missus doesn't know him,
then we'll have to dig deep.
[IRENE]
There he is.
‐‐[WATSON] Who's that?
‐‐[IRENE] Tony Shigeru.
They call him the don
of the publishing world.
He knows everything that
happens in print media,
and everybody involved.
[WATSON] Ah, right, Milverton
was a journalist!
[TONY] And what could
have put me on the radar
of the notorious Irene Adler?
I need information
on a Milverton.
I see. What's it worth to you?
How much do you want?
[TONY] If you have
to ask, don't bother.
[IRENE] Hmm. How about a juicy
scoop on the mayor?
Moran lied about his education.
That is juicy indeed.
Your man Milverton is one of
the most accomplished
blackmailers I know of.
A blackmailer?
[TONY] He digs up dirt on
celebrities and politicians,
and they pay him
to bury it again.
All while operating
under the guise
of a legitimate entrepreneur.
Of what kind?
[TONY]
Several.
He runs a variety
of front operations
using multiple
assumed identities.
I'll send a list along later.
[WATSON]
Can you tell us where he lives?
[TONY] Hmm. From what I'm told,
he's set himself up a bed
in the office of one of
his front companies.
That said, I have no idea
which company or where it is.
Then we'll have
to run down the whole list.
[TONY] I'm also informed
he's been paying nightly visits
to a certain old hangout of his.
Lastly, his appearance
has changed dramatically
since his time as a reporter.
In fact the difference was
so stark that I was inspired
to write a poem after I saw it.
[WATSON]
Uh, what do you mean by that?
How badly do
you wanna know, kid?
[WATSON]
Uhh...
How's this?
A scoop on yours truly.
Would Moran use his
measurements as a password?
Of course not.
Why would he even know them?
So what is it?
[EMIRI giggling]
[laptop beeping]
‐‐Ahh!
‐‐Buu‐buu!
Hey, don't do that to my laptop!
[gasps]
Hey! Give it back!
Gimme! Let go!
‐‐[EMIRI whimpering]
‐‐Oh, crap!
Uh, c'mon, please don't cry!
[SHERLOCK gruntin]
‐‐Ha! Piggy! Let's go, Mr. Pig!
‐‐[squealing]
[elephant trumpets]
Ugh! This blows...
We searched the whole
town and we've got jack
and crap to show for it.
[SHERLOCK chuckles]
[phone ringing]
[WATSON] This is the "certain
old hangout" that Mr. Shigeru
mentioned, right, Ms. Adler?
Yes, that's right.
[WATSON]
I've taken a look around,
but I haven't seen anyone
matching his description.
Also, that poem he gave
us tells me less than nothing.
[IRENE] Complaining
doesn't help us either.
Of course! I'll leave you to it.
Get after that girl working...
[WATSON]
Dark skin, round ears.
‐‐[MILVERTON] Got it?
‐‐[gasps]
[WATSON]
Light skin, round ears!
From light to dark.
Like an Othello game!
[MILVERTON]
But not here! Now go tell her!
‐‐She's losing me money.
‐‐Ms. Adler!
I think I found Milverton!
Meet me in
Sherlock's room tomorrow.
Good job.
Stay on the ball, there.
‐‐[IRENE] Excuse me, sir.
‐‐Huh?
[IRENE]
I'm with Kabuki Insurance.
You're the proprietor here, yes?
This is about your policy.
The Smile Plan.
[MILVERTON snoring]
[BAR PATRON 8A]
Whoa, check her out.
That's Agatha Kuroki!
[IRENE gasps]
[BAR PATRON 8B]
Oh, yeah, she had that affair!
Your payment for the month is
due tonight, as agreed upon.
[AGATHA]
Just a little longer, please.
[STAFF 8A]
No way.
The boss doesn't give
extensions for anything.
You've got less than an hour.
[AGATHA] Wait. I'll get
him his money. Please!
[IRENE]
How much do you need?
Ah‐‐ [gasps] Irene...?
It's been awhile, hasn't it?
Since we shared the screen.
It has...
What were you doing in that bar?
I'll pay you back. Promise.
It's fine.
Milverton knows something
that would ruin me
if it made it into the papers.
In exchange for his silence,
he demanded monthly payments‐‐
My money and my body.
But the tabloids learned
I'd slept with him.
Now the money's drying up.
Then stop paying him,
or it'll never end.
But...
[IRENE] You can't win
if you play his game.
Trust me on this.
I'll always have your back.
Thank you. That means a lot.
I feel a little better now.
[SHERLOCK]
Why are you here?
Oh, don't mind me.
[WATSON] Ah? It looks like
Emiri forgot her picture book.
[doorbell rings]
‐‐[WATSON] Hello?
‐‐[IRENE] Come in, it's open!
[door creaks
[BOTH gasp]
[WATSON]
Milverton!
[MILVERTON]
Huh?
[IRENE]
I told him to come here.
[MILVERTON]
Yeah, and you'd better believe
that took me by surprise.
Getting a phone call out of
the blue from some broad
‐‐I never even met.
‐‐[sniffing]
What the hell are you doing?
This pig smells.
‐‐[MILVERTON growls]
‐‐It's time to talk business.
For instance, hiring underage
girls to work at your bar.
What are you goin' on about?
Yeah, these customers all love
the young girls.
Mine are mostly
middle schoolers,
a few high schoolers in there.
College chicks may
as well be grannies!
Hold on, it's you!
Now, we can discuss
Yui Shirota's medical chart.
I get it. My ex
put you up to all this.
Well, go ahead and show
that video to the cops
‐‐if you feel like it.
‐‐[WATSON] Uh?
You think the police
in this town are
gonna do anything about it, pal?
I could build an island in
the bay outta half the dirt
I got on those punks,
are you kidding me?
Ah. Well if that's the case,
I suppose we should
try another approach.
Knock yourself out,
sweet cheeks.
Right. Agatha made her
payment to you yesterday,
so why did you still
go public with her secret?
She missed her
payment deadline
by five seconds. We're done.
[SHERLOCK]
Tell me something, pig.
[MILVERTON]
Screw you.
Who do you plan
on selling Emiri to?
Well, look at
the big brain on this guy.
I've got a friend with
a whole lot of money
and he likes 'em real young.
A man of his stature could give
my daughter a much better life
than her basket case
of a mother, right?
Whattaya gonna do?
Can you believe that scumbag?!
Hey! We're getting that chart!
We know where it must be.
Yes, in Milverton's office.
[WATSON]
Hmm.
[SHERLOCK] We found the pig
we were looking for, old man,
but where's his sty?
Come on, can't you
try to figure it out
for yourself before you ask me?
Tell me you at least
noticed that stink on him.
What are we watching right now?
Forensic rakugo.
You were picking up chlorine.
While you're at it, did you
get a look at his eyes?
Yeah, things were redder
than a monkey's ass cheeks!
Boy, you're a real class act.
Point is, if his eyes were red‐‐
It's at a night pool.
Milverton has the chart
locked up in the office
at his night pool.
Let's go find it.
[WATSON]
Oh, right. Coming!
Ah! Maki. Um...
Could you sign this?
Huh? Why do you have that?
[SWIMMERS chatting, laughing]
And the office is...
Over here.
[WATSON chuckles]
[SHERLOCK]
There it is.
[WATSON] Of course
there's extra security.
Great. How do we deal with that?
[WATSON]
Ah. Hmm?
Do you have an idea?
Um... What?
[SHERLOCK]
Go make a scene.
‐‐[WATSON] Ahh! You jerk!
‐‐[SWIMMERS screaming]
‐‐Hey!
‐‐What the hell are you doing?!
[GUARD 8A]
Out of the pool, now!
[GUARD 8B]
You're done here, pervert!
Oh, my. You are a bold one.
[SHERLOCK]
Looks like we found it.
Now where's that treasure?
Excellent question.
Thinking back, the stink
of chlorine on that pig
was incredibly strong when
he came to the office before.
Right? My nose hairs
were burning.
[SHERLOCK] He wouldn't reek
like that just from sleeping
near a pool.
He'd have to have been soaking
in the water every single night.
[gasps]
[IRENE] You'd like to hear
how I knew, wouldn't you?
[IRENE] An old friend
of mine told me about it.
[MILVERTON]
What the hell is this crap?
I'm paying you idiots
to guard the damn door.
[MILVERTON]
No shit. Do your jobs.
Huh?
[SHERLOCK] Jugemu jugemu goko
no surikire kaijarisuigyo‐no
suigyomats unraimats furaimats
kuunerutokoro ni sumutokoro
yabura...
[SHERLOCK] Ponpokona
no chokyumei no chosuke.
Hey. Shut up!
[SHERLOCK grunting]
[door clacks]
[MILVERTON]
Huh? What do you want?
‐‐[gun clicks]
‐‐[MILVERTON gasps] Ah! No.
No, don't! Don't do it!
[gunshots]
[door slams
[gasps]
Ponpokopi!
It's time to go.
[SWIMMERS murmurin]
[SWIMMER 8A]
What happened? What's going on?
[SWIMMER 8B] They're saying
someone got murdered!
[SWIMMER 8A]
Holy crap! Do we know who died?
[SWIMMER 8C]
Nope!
[AGATHA grunting]
Who's there? Ah! Irene?
Don't get caught, okay, Agatha?
I believe this is
what you came for.
[IRENE]
Now get going.
You've done enough.
Those people's secrets
are all safe now.
[IRENE]
You got everything you wanted.
There's no reason for you
to be here anymore.
So run. Don't look back.
Or else, I'll turn
you in myself.
Thank you.
[lighter clicks]
Bless you.
Thank you so much for
keeping my little girl safe.
I don't know how
I can repay you.
Piggy.
Thank you!
Let's play again soon!
Pfft. Yeah. Let's not.
Emiri, we should be going.
I can show you out.
[EMIRI]
Bye‐bye! See ya later!
What a peach.
I think Irene may see
a bit of herself in Emiri.
‐‐[EMIRI] Thank you!
‐‐[WATSON] You think? Maybe so.
What makes you say that?
[WATSON]
Read this.
[HUDSON] Someone's been
talking to the gossip rags.
[WATSON]
Irene went to them herself.
Even as a kid, she always
marched to her own beat.
[WATSON]
Hmm?
[HUDSON]
I suppose I never told you,
but I looked after
her for a while.
[gasps]
[LESTRADE] Do you think
you can help me out with this?
Let's find out.
Victim's name is Milverton.
Killed last night.
Cause of death was
two gunshots to the chest.
[SHERLOCK]
That's going nowhere.
[LESTRADE]
What do you mean by that?
Way too many suspects.
[WATSON gasps]
[phone buzzing
[LESTRADE]
This is Lestrade.
There was?!
Jack's struck again!
I'll be there as soon as I can!
[HUDSON]
The real thing?
Seems so.
The victim was a woman.
An actress who's been
in the news lately.
Her name was Agatha Kuroki.
I need to report to the
crime scene immediately.
What's wrong?
[IRENE whimpers]
[gaspin]
[IRENE gasps]
Irene.
Somebody is trying
to kill you, right?
Jack the Ripper.
[FUYUTO] I know a special
place that I'd really
like to show you.
[MAKI] I'll be by your side
until the very end!