[WATSON] Six months ago,
I was performing an autopsy
on a certain young woman.
I came across something
that looked like a sticker.
I didn't think much
of it at the time,
then recently, I found out that
it was a miniaturized
transmitter.
I reported this
information to my boss,
and suddenly, it seemed
like my life was in danger.
[WATSON gasps]
[tires screeching]
[WATSON grunts]
[WATSON] I had to leave
the West Side behind.
[WATSON] The only way
I can return to my old life
is to find out
who wanted me dead,
and I need this
man's help to do it.
But...
[SHERLOCK]
Hey! Hurry up and make dinner.
Coming right up.
[WATSON]
He has yet to ask about my case,
and I'm not sure he ever will.
[FUYUTO]
This is Shinjuku's West Side.
A tidy grid of well‐lit streets,
teeming with smiling citizens,
walled off from the
morass of crime and chaos
swirling just to the east.
There, on the dark
streets of Kabukicho,
where the trumpeting of
elephants rings in the hour
and evil lurks in every
shadow, six detectives roam.
Freaks, geeks, losers,
and loons to a one.
Where they roam,
chaos will surely follow.
And you, babies, are invited
to watch their wild war
of wills and wits.
[GROUP]
Happy Birthday, Moriarty!
Thanks, guys!
[MICHEL]
So how old are you now, kid?
[MORIARTY]
I'm 16.
You have the smell of a winner,
same as I do, James.
Guys like you don't
belong in this dump.
You should head
to the West Side.
Yeah, this dump
is for guys like you.
[FUYUTO] Hmph. Soon, I'll put
the East Side behind me,
Jack the Ripper behind bars, and
300,000,000 yen in my pocket.
No, thanks.
Oh, yeah, that guy.
Been a while since he came up.
That one turned out
to be a fake, right?
[MICHEL] The last we saw of the
real Jack was six months ago.
That was when
they found the body
of Ward Mayor Moran's
daughter, Alexandra.
Can't say I'm a fan of Moran's,
but that girl was pretty hot.
[bells jingle]
[DIANA]
Happy birthday!
[MORIARTY]
Huh?
A gift, from all of us.
[MORIARTY laughs]
I can't wait!
[FUYUTO]
Hmm?
[gasping]
[DIANA] It's your own homemade
girly mag featuring us!
I know you teens love to fap!
Thanks a bunch!
Uh... Miss Maki?
Just in case you wanted to know,
my birthday's November 12th.
'Kay.
[PIPE meows]
Hey, speaking of girls...
You got a girlfriend, Morty?
Nope, sure don't.
[GIRL 2B] Then how come you've
got a bunch of pressed flowers
stashed away in your notebook?
[MARY]
Seriously?
I wouldn't have thought
you had a romantic side!
Hold on!
They're only clovers,
and they're for my sister!
[MARY]
For real?
[MORIARTY]
Yes, for real!
[KOBAYASHI]
Wait, you've got a sister?
That kid...
He does seem like he has
quite a way with people.
[MORIARTY] No way!
Why would I want to do that?
[KOBAYASHI] Aw, c'mon, Jim.
We're all friends here.
[HUDSON]
Oh, Johnny‐baby!
Yes?
[HUDSON] Could your stuff
be out of the storeroom
by this weekend?
‐‐Uh...
‐‐I need it back.
My walk‐in closet
is going there.
Have you thought about
moving in with Sherlock?
[WATSON gulps]
Thank you, sweetie!
‐‐[knocking]
‐‐[HUDSON] Hmm?
Who's that?
We're closed down
for a private event!
‐‐[PU] Anybody!
‐‐[HUDSON] Ugh,
‐‐would you please settle down?
‐‐[PU] Is anyone in there?!
[HUDSON]
The Pipe Cat is closed today,
so if you'd kindly
stop pounding on‐‐
[gasps
I'm begging you! Please help me!
Dear me! By all means, come in.
We're so glad you
found us, young man,
‐‐because we have a thrilling...
‐‐[MARY] Whatcha lookin' at?
I've seen him before.
Where was it?
[gulpin]
You knocked that right back.
So, are you feeling better?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
But the police are after me.
Oh! I saw him on the news!
They said he killed
the owner of Gachoen!
Gachoen?!
You mean the same Gachoen
that has legendary rocker B‐zo
for their mascot
and resident artist?
Yeah, that super fancy
hotel on the West Side.
Soft beds, three‐star eats,
and a liberal in‐and‐out policy,
know what I'm sayin'?
How vile.
[PU]
So you saw that.
Here's my card.
[HUDSON] Hmm. Oh, a lawyer.
And your name is‐‐
[KOBAYASHI]
Hmm?
[HUDSON]
"Kiguma"?
Please just call me Pu.
[HUDSON]
Right. Continue, Pu.
Pu?
Last night,
I was up in my office on
the West Side like always.
Then, around 8 o'clock, I got
a call from my Uncle Cosmos.
[MARY]
Uncle Cosmos?
Yeah.
It's written like "Outer Space,"
but it's pronounced "Cosmos."
My dad's name
is written like "Earth,"
but it's pronounced "Gaia."
That's quite a tradition.
[PU] My uncle called to
tell me that he had been
diagnosed with cancer.
He wanted to write me into his
will as the sole beneficiary.
[PU] He never had
any children of his own.
[PU] We had a few drinks
on the balcony while
he wrote up his will.
But I must have had too much.
I passed out,
and when I woke up‐‐
[PU gasps]
[PU] Uncle Cosmos
was covered in blood.
[gasps]
[PU gasps]
Everybody, freeze!
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[GREGORY] Pu Tanaka,
you are under arrest for murder.
[HUDSON] That hardly
seems necessary, Officer.
No. It wasn't me!
[GREGORY]
Take him away.
I didn't do it, sir!
Please, you have to believe me!
Let me go!
Inspector Lestrade,
that sweet young man
is far too handsome
to be a murderer.
Mrs. Hudson.
This is official police
business, and I have to ask‐‐
Uh! Ah!
‐‐[GREGORY whimpers]
‐‐You like that?
Feels nice, doesn't it?
[GREGORY] Yes, it does!
It feels so, so nice...
There's a good boy.
[GREGORY whimpers]
Now then.
The client today is yours truly.
This is an S‐ranker,
five million with bonus.
I don't think that
Pu guy is really my type.
Pass on this one.
[MICHEL] What's the case look
like on your end, Inspector?
Ninety percent
chance of conviction.
If those are
the odds we're playing,
I'd prefer to sit
out this round.
I trust your judgment.
If Beezy's a part of this.
I have no choice but to take it!
[HUDSON] After the sun has
set upon the rest of the world,
our town of Kabukicho
lights up in neon.
If gold and silver
are what you're after,
then get out there and bring
back my precious Pooh bear!
A light gleams
in these men's eyes.
This is a haven for
outcasts and oddballs.
And you're the
reason they call it
"the Detectives' Row House."
Mm... mwah!
The winner will be the one
who can prove Pu's innocence.
Bring that big pot o' honey
straight back to mama.
Give me Pu!
[GUARD 3A]
Hurry it up!
[GUARD 3B]
Come on, shitbags!
‐‐Psht.
‐‐I hear over on the West Side,
they don't treat
people like livestock.
Yeah, 'cause Mayor Moran's a pig
that can walk on two feet.
Hey!
But that's impressive
by pig standards!
A malcontent, huh?
You get a full search.
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm kidding, he's great!
Moran's the best!
Long live Moran!
[WATSON]
This is the place.
[SHERLOCK]
Move on.
Move on where?
There's no way
we can make it through
that hideous gate.
Sorry?
It's an inconvenience, but we
don't have a choice if we‐‐
Yes, we do.
[gasps]
[SHERLOCK] We can go back along
the path you took to get here.
[FUYUTO]
The man himself. Right here?
[GREGORY] Yes, Mister B‐zo
was a personal friend
of the late Cosmos Tanaka.
And last night, as it hap‐‐
I'm honored to meet you, sir!
I'm the Row House's
greatest investigator.
Kyogoku Fuyuto's my name!
[B‐ZO] You've got a
grasp of the language,
but if your words are too stiff,
then your heart's gonna
harden up as well, yeah?
Break that shell, baby.
Forgive me. I just...
I'm standing here
in front of my idol!
Oh, I'm your idol, you say?
Yeah!
My childhood friend
gave me a copy
of this book as a gift.
And these pages taught me
everything I know
about being a real man!
Your book is what made me
realize that there's
a whole wide world beyond
the ugliness and chaos
of the East Side.
It's how I learned about
the beauties that await me
if I take life on
at full throttle!
I consider you my
mentor‐‐no, my master!
On your wisdom,
Fuyuto will rise!
It feels so great to hear
you say that, my baby!
I'm always happy to see the
seeds I've planted taking bloom.
[gasps]
[FUYUTO sighs, gasps]
He touched me, he touched me!
He shook my hand!
I'm never gonna wash it again!
[GREGORY] Could you
please give us your account
of what happened
last night, Mr. B‐zo?
Okay. Cozzy and Pu
were sitting out here.
They'd finished working on
the will and started drinking.
I thought about
asking to join them,
but it felt like I would be
interrupting a family thing.
Now, I...
If only I hadn't been
so scared of seeming rude.
[FUYUTO whimpers]
I'll take over from here.
After he finished
writing up the will,
Cosmos had a bit too much
to drink and passed out
on the table.
And while he was unconscious,
Pu pulled a steak knife
out of the roast
and drove it into his back!
[GREGORY] When the fire died,
our investigation revealed
a charred body believed to
be that of Cosmos Tanaka,
and a personal item of Pu's,
which was covered in blood.
But is there some
possibility a third party
did it? Any at all?
[B‐ZO]
Sorry, there's no way.
There wasn't anybody else
on the security tapes.
[GREGORY] There doesn't seem
to be any way around it.
Everything we've seen
points to Pu as our killer.
Killing his client minutes
after they wrote him
into their will.
That seems like a pretty
stupid move for an attorney.
Well, either way,
if we're able to find
the murder weapon
B‐zo described,
then that's the end of it.
Pardon me. You two came
to ask about Pu, right?
[WATSON]
Uh. Yes, ma'am.
Let's see...
What can you tell us about
Cosmos and Pu's relationship?
[HIROKO]
Cosmos was my husband's brother.
The two of them didn't talk
much, but he and Pu were close.
And I can hardly
imagine anything, um,
happening between them?
[SHERLOCK] You had these bills
from several loan sharks.
What did your son and
husband need with this money?
Prostitutes? Gambling?
[HIROKO grunts]
[SHERLOCK]
Then it was gambling.
[HIROKO]
I‐I'm sorry. What does that‐‐
I have to poop.
[HIROKO] The bathroom
is at the end of the hall,
on the right side.
Sorry, my friend
can be a little bit odd.
But rest assured, Mrs. Tanaka.
I guarantee you that Pu's case
is in the best of hands now.
‐‐[HIROKO] Our poor little boy.
‐‐[WATSON] Hmm?
[HIROKO] Pu always wanted to be
a doctor when he was young.
But he couldn't stand the sight
of blood, so he went into law.
Killing Cosmos with a knife?
I can't even imagine...
[SHERLOCK]
Hmm...
[FUYUTO humming]
[gasps]
[FUYUTO]
Hmm...
[GREGORY] Really? Definitive
proof of the killer's identity.
Kyogoku. Please fill us in.
Sure, babe.
This one quick call
will explain it all.
[receiver ringing]
[HIROKO] Hello, you've reached
the Tanaka residence.
Hey, girl!
Sorry‐‐ Good afternoon, ma'am.
I'm Kyogoku with
the West Side police.
[HIROKO]
Oh, is this about my Pu?
[FUYUTO]
Yes, ma'am.
We wanted to tell you that Pu
has been released from custody.
[HIROKO] He's free?
I'm so happy to hear that!
There's something
I would like to know.
During the time leading up
to Cosmos's death,
had he invited Gaia
and Pu to go gambling?
[HIROKO]
Uh... Well...
[FUYUTO] And that drove
them deep into debt,
or am I mistaken?
[HIROKO] You're not. He twisted
their arms to go with him.
And forced them to keep playing.
[FUYUTO] That's an ugly thing
to do to his family, isn't it?
[HIROKO]
I agree. I hate to admit it,
but a part of me feels that
he got what he deserved.
I'm glad to hear you
say so, Mrs. Tanaka.
Thank you for your cooperation.
There it is.
A clear motive for
Pu and his mother
in the murder of Cosmos Tanaka.
[gasps]
The numbers listed
under these names correspond
to amounts outstanding
on various loans.
And I've called several
lenders to verify this myself.
[gasps]
So, now. I shall
make my declaration.
The culprit in this case
can only be Pu Tanaka.
Ya feel me?
Huh? But I thought
the assignment was to prove
that Pu didn't kill Cosmos.
It was indeed.
And if you want to know why
I would pass up the money,
it's simple. Because justice!
[WATSON]
I see.
[B‐ZO] That's real.
Mad respect for your man here.
[FUYUTO] I know nothing
in life but to be legit.
[GREGORY] Well, Mister Holmes,
if the lack of a motive
was part of your concern,
it seems that we can
safely put that aside.
Pu had more than enough.
From there,
all we have to do is find
the murder weapon.
Then, I'm afraid this case
will be as good as solved.
I don't think
this is going to help‐‐
Shut up! Pu didn't do it.
There's no way he did it.
Pu's not stupid enough to leave
such an obvious clue!
He can't be!
Yeah, I agree.
He struck me as
a pretty smart guy, too.
He's a lawyer and, at one point,
he was looking to
become a doctor.
What are you talking about?
That was what
his mother told me.
He went into law because
he couldn't stand
the sight of blood.
She said there's no way he could
take a knife to another person.
[SHERLOCK] The police haven't
said anything publicly
about the murder weapon.
And that means‐‐
[WATSON]
Uh?
The knife?
[SHERLOCK]
Before Pu came to the row house,
he took this knife home and
handed it off to his mother.
You mean, he's the killer?
[FUYUTO] There's no point
in delaying this further.
Now admit your mistake...
and let's be done with it.
[SHERLOCK] And what mistake
would I be admitting?
‐‐[cell phone ringing]
‐‐That's obvious!
After Pu did the deed, he had
to come through this room
on his way out the door.
And he dropped that
murder weapon right there.
‐‐Yeah, baby.
‐‐[gasps]
[B‐ZO] Give me five
and I'll call you back
when all this business
is over with.
[Always good to know you
have a friend, right, buddy?
[Pardon me for asking,
Mr. Holmes.
But I'd really like to know
what's in your pocket there.
'Cause to me,
it looked like a knife.
Maybe even the one used
to kill my friend Cosmos.
‐‐[FUYUTO] It did?
‐‐Your right coat pocket.
[gasps]
[FUYUTO] Then it's time
to close this case... perhaps.
Let's see...
What're you hiding
in your pocket?
[WATSON gulps]
[gasps]
[gaspin]
And... what part of this
looks like a knife to you?
That's, ah‐‐
You weren't in the room when
I put my hand in my pocket.
What made you think
I was holding anything?
And why would you
guess that it was a knife?
The same one that killed Cosmos?
[B‐ZO whimpers]
[WATSON]
I'm lost. What's going on here?
You wanna know?
Uh! Oh, boy, do I ever!
So tell me all about it!
[giggles]
Hey, old man.
Quit grasping at
straws already, would ya?
Any idiot could tell ya
that Pu got Cosmos drunk
and stuck a knife in him.
The whole story
points straight to that!
Ugh. But the problem is...
...if any idiot could tell you,
then it's too obvious
to be true.
Well, if Pu hadn't done it,
then who done did it,
huh, smart guy?
A few things
caught my attention,
like the love letters from
Cosmos that Pu's mother
was keeping stashed inside
a drawer back in her bedroom.
So he was carrying
a torch for her?
But in the end, she fell
for his little brother.
Pu's old man, Gaia.
Such is life, right?
Well, not that
that wasn't a sad story
and everything, but how 'bout
you get back to the point
and tell us who killed
Cosmos already?
So he had the hots
for his sister‐in‐law,
who cares?
It's not like his brother's
the dead one here, right?
That might be
the official story,
but I'm not sure I buy it.
Huh?! They found
his burned‐up body.
They certainly did find
somebody's burned‐up body.
There you go
splitting hairs again!
Cosmos and Pu were
the only ones in the room,
and Pu's still
got his body, so...
...that crispy critter
couldn't have been
anybody but Cosmos!
I suspect that the charred
corpse they found
was actually Pu's father, Gaia.
[B‐ZO whimpers]
Cosmos had been
allowing Gaia to stay at Gachoen
in secret, under the
pretext of hiding him
from the loan sharks.
He called Pu up
to the hotel and got him
passed‐out drunk, dressed up
Gaia's corpse to look like
it was his own, stuck the
knife in Pu's hands,
and then lit the fire.
Pu woke up in
the middle of a fire with
a bloody knife in his
hands and ran away.
And that's the whole story.
Hmm... All right, so where
the hell'd Cosmos get to?
B‐zo was right‐‐
I did put the knife
in my pocket earlier.
But he never saw that.
Only somebody in the room with
me could have known about it.
[WATSON]
Hmm...
[SHERLOCK]
Hmph! You got a point there.
Wha‐‐?! But how did B‐zo
figure it out, then?
Obviously, he heard
it from Cosmos.
They were on the phone.
[FUYUTO]
Shut up!
If you're saying Cosmos
was the killer,
then I say bring him here!
Show me the money!
[SHERLOCK]
You want to see him right now?
Yes! Right here, right now!
[SHERLOCK] I would be
more than happy to oblige.
[COSMOS gasps, screams]
[FUYUTO gasps]
I understand that you
owed him quite a bit of money
as well, B‐zo.
That's the reason you agreed to
take part in this hideous farce.
[B‐ZO sighs]
Party's over. Time to clear out.
Oh, my god...!
[SHERLOCK] How's peeping
on a stranger's hotel room
like getting caught dead
to rights for murder?
Why don't you tell me.
In the end,
somebody's gonna get boned.
Been saving that?
[SHERLOCK] That's all the
time we have for today.
[HUDSON] Pu Bear. We need to
have a talk about our future.
Excuse me?
I'll get right to the point.
We can't just ignore
this age gap.
What age gap?
[FUYUTO groans]
Farewell... B‐zo...
[SHERLOCK]
Why aren't you cleaning yet?!
[WATSON]
Uh?
There's a schedule,
start following it already!
Your share of the
apartment is from that end
of the sofa to this end,
so don't dangle your feet.
Understood.
Can we please talk
about my case?
After I told my boss,
I noticed someone watching
me from behind‐‐
[SHERLOCK]
Never mind, get out!