[knocking]
[ALEX]
Come in!
How's it going,
Alex? Feeling okay?
[ALEX sighs]
[ALEX] This boredom...
I think it might kill me!
[growls]
[laughs]
[MORIARTY] Look.
Another one for the collection.
You really love
the East Side, don't you?
I can't wait to see it
myself someday.
The doctor said that
your condition has been
getting a lot better lately.
It'll be soon.
I know you're going to love all
of the folks at the row house.
And you'll get to
meet Sherlock, too.
[gasps]
I don't think I could ask for
a better Christmas
present than that!
[PARTYGOERS murmuring]
[ALEX gasps, yelps]
Ow...
Hey, are you okay?
[ALEX]
Hmph.
[MORIARTY sighs]
[knocking]
[MORAN]
James? Are you in there?
Dad's here.
You need to hurry up.
You know where to go, right?
Don't forget!
‐‐[ALEX] Hmm.
‐‐[MORIARTY] One more thing‐‐
This looks better on you.
Don't be scared.
I'll catch up to you soon,
I promise.
Thanks, Moriarty.
[MORIARTY gasps]
What's wrong?
Surprised I know
your street name?
[ALEX giggles]
Where've you been, James?
The guests are expecting you.
I apologize.
I haven't been
feeling very well, sir.
Fortunately, you still have time
to make your appearance.
Right.
[MORIARTY panting]
[laughs]
Ah...
[gasps]
[MORIARTY]
A‐Alex?
Wake up...
Alex?
Come on...
[MORIARTY]
Alex...?
[MORIARTY whimpers]
[sobbing]
[MORIARTY]
Whoever did this will pay.
[WATSON grunts]
[gasps]
[FUYUTO]
Did that get your attention?
[WATSON gasps]
[FUYUTO] Now give me the drive
so that I can catch Jack
and make my name!
Does that mean it was you?
[FUYUTO groans]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[SHERLOCK]
Good job, Watson.
You did something right.
[MORIARTY chuckles]
[SHERLOCK]
Hmph.
Why are you here?
[FUYUTO pants, screams]
[screams, grunts]
[WATSON gasps]
Is that Irene?
[IRENE]
Hm.
But how...? You were dead!
[SHERLOCK sniffing]
[WATSON grunts]
Someone, explain.
Sorry. It was a bunch of lies.
She's not in any danger
as long as she's here,
but that doesn't get us
any closer to Jack's identity.
What a waste.
Do you have a plan, then?
The drive is what
Jack's really after,
and for all he
knows you have it.
I think we ought to use
that to bait him out.
You make that
sound rather simple.
[MORIARTY] First, we needed
to get Irene to a place
where Jack would easily
be able to attack her.
But at the same time,
we couldn't make it so obvious
that he would realize
it was a trap.
Ugh. The kitchen, too?
[MORIARTY] We needed you
to leak the information
so that Jack would
hear about it.
Did he find the drive?
[MORIARTY] And of course,
he showed up just as planned.
[MORIARTY] But he used you
as a diversion to get Sherlock
away from Irene.
It's over!
Lie face down with
your hands on your head!
[MORIARTY]
Wh‐What are you doing?!
[LESTRADE]
Hurry up.
We got an anonymous tip
that Jack had caught Irene
and was holding
her in captivity.
Do you have anything
to say to us about that?
[MORIARTY] And he tricked
Lestrade into coming after me,
leaving Irene wide open.
[MORIARTY gasps]
That's him!
[alarm blares]
What now?!
Move it!
[LESTRADE grunts, screams]
[MORIARTY panting]
[IRENE whimpering]
[gasps]
Hang on, Irene!
[IRENE groans]
He ran out the front.
[WATSON]
Ms. Adler!
[MORIARTY gasps]
It's Jack! You stay here
and look after her!
I'm sorry.
This happened because
I let my guard down.
No, it wasn't anybody's fault.
Jack was one step ahead of us.
It's a risk we all accepted
in making this plan.
So, where do we go from here?
I've already set
the next step in motion.
Thing is...
[MORIARTY]
Don't worry about it.
Slow down.
Don't worry about what?
We still have the USB drive,
and Watson doesn't know anything
except for what you've told him.
The bait is already on the hook.
Now if Irene can be dead for
a while, we can catch our fish.
[SHERLOCK sighs]
[MORIARTY] If Irene was dead
and Sherlock had the drive,
Jack would have to adjust
his strategy to a harder target,
meaning more chances
for him to mess up.
And we expected he'd
target you as his source
of information, which
would make it easier for us
to predict his next move.
So, we kept you in the dark,
knowing you'd be suspicious
of me for showing up
‐‐at the safehouse.
‐‐[WATSON gasps]
[MORIARTY] Anyone would,
considering the timing
and the fact I wasn't
supposed to know about it.
And then, we used your
suspicion to draw Jack in.
Irene put a lot of work
into her little magic show,
and it turned out
exactly like we hoped.
She had you convinced that
I was going to attack Sherlock
and steal the drive,
and we knew Jack would
figure that out quick.
Once he did,
his next obvious move
would be to manipulate you
into going to Sherlock's place
and taking the drive for him.
[WATSON]
How could you do that?
[MORIARTY]
Ah.
[WATSON sniffing]
Whoa. Wait!
[SHERLOCK grunts]
Damn you. I thought
you were gonna be killed!
But you... You made it all up!
I'm sorry, John.
Please, know that Sherlock
never wanted to use you‐‐
We couldn't think of any
other way to lure Jack out.
[MORIARTY]
Mm‐hmm!
But still! I was so scared.
I thought... I thought I was
about to lose someone else!
[sobbing softly]
Sorry.
[gasps]
U‐Uh... Um...
That may be the first
time I've ever heard
an apology from Sherlock.
[WATSON sniffs]
Tell me.
Why get involved
in this case, Moriarty?
You're putting
yourself in danger,
and you're not a detective.
We call him Moriarty
on the East Side.
He was born James Moran.
[gasps]
Moran?
You mean... He's‐‐
[SHERLOCK] He's the son
of our esteemed mayor.
And the twin brother of
his late daughter Alexandra.
Jack's last victim before
his recent reappearance.
Ah... Now I see.
[FUYUTO groaning]
So this Jack guy...
He seems like
a whole heap of crazy.
He butchers humans
and makes angels out of them.
Does he fancy himself
a demon or a god?
Or something else?
Is... Is that a riddle, o‐or
are you trying to sound cool?
‐‐[FUYUTO grunts]
‐‐Now, let's get going.
The stage is set and
the audience is waiting.
[ROW HOUSE murmuring]
[MICHEL] Are you really trying
to tell me that Kyogoku's
been Jack the whole time?
Nah, I can't imagine him
killing anybody like that.
It's hard to picture Sherlock
screwing up this bad,
but I don't know
what else it could be.
[CHINKILL]
Ooh, this place is packed!
[DIANE]
Party time! What's the occasion?
I guess you'll find out soon!
Ah‐‐ Pardon me, Ms. Maki.
No.
[MORIARTY] Here's a little
something as an apology.
[MAKI]
Ah. Thank you.
[CHINKILL]
Hey, Maki, get over here!
Ah?
That's Kyogoku!
Wait a minute...
What's this about?
It's Sherlock.
According to him,
Go‐Go is really Jack the Ripper.
Huh?! Are you kidding me?
That's ridiculous!
It's okay.
Don't you worry, Maki.
I'm sure they'll
clear this up soon.
Could you get her
a glass of water, please?
Thank you so much.
[gasping]
Hey, old man! How's it been?
Weird day, right?
How do you mean?
I've been hearing that
they finally brought in
Jack the Ripper!
Ah. Is that what you meant?
Eh, Kyogoku was rambling on
like a man possessed
about how he was gonna
be the one to put Jack
behind bars. Heh! Turns out
it was him the whole time!
Wait a minute...
Just because he's up here
with his hands tied
doesn't mean that he's Jack.
Okay, fair enough, okay.
But what about the crazed
bloodshot eyes and the whole
"Jumping Watson
with a knife" thing?
That may have
had something to do
with the peyote
I smelled on his breath.
And that would also
explain the dilated pupils.
Most likely someone dosed
him without him knowing.
I get it!
What's a peyote?
A cactus native to Mexico.
It synthesizes
a drug called mescaline,
a powerful hallucinogen
with similar effects
to LSD or psilocybes,
one that could easily
drive a person to kill,
in the right set
of circumstances.
How'd he get himself
drugged with something like that
and not know?!
Seriously, what kind of
a moron would you have to be?
Hey now, cut the kid some slack.
There are two things
in the world that can
drive any man insane:
Money and love.
‐‐[MARY gasps]
‐‐[SHERLOCK] Love, huh?
Come to think of it, if someone
offered that guy a cure
for his chronic virginity,
I bet he'd do pretty much
anything to get it.
[KOBAYASHI]
Where you going, Michel?
Did you figure
something out or what?
What's with them?
But still, I don't think
the ladies around here,
uh, tend to have
that effect on guys‐‐
[gasps]
Wait, did Irene seduce him?!
Not even close.
She's been busy recovering
from a nasty stab wound.
Hah! Yeah, true enough.
Eh, fine then, screw it.
Guess I'll leave the mystery
solving to the pros.
[DIANE]
Okay. What was that about?
Come on! How ya gonna
walk out of your own show?
It's a lie... There's no way...
It's a lie!
[SHERLOCK]
Don't give up yet.
We know that the information
that eventually led Jack
to Irene originally
came from Watson.
Meaning it must
have passed through
someone he knows in town:
a row house tenant
or a Pipe Cat regular.
[gasps]
Of course!
Kobayashi, that prick!
That's what you're going with?
What kinda complex
does someone gotta have
to murder good‐looking people
and chop off their sexy parts?!
I'm no shrink,
but I've read some articles!
Kobayashi's got a face
like an over‐the‐hill boxer
and a dick like a newborn.
Check and check!
Walk it back a bit.
Jack's MO was to remove
his victims' genitals
and use their blood
to paint wings around them.
He was trying to turn
their bodies into
something beautiful,
winged, and sexless.
Angels, in other words.
What if his killings weren't
done out of hatred,
but rather some perverse
desire to turn the victims
into more perfect beings?
Well, if that's how it is,
then why'd he always take
the wombs with him and leave
the wangs rotting at the scene?
If Jack's perfect being
has no junk at all,
what's with the
uterus collection?
Here's the kicker:
In his mind, having
neither and having both
aren't much different.
It's having only one
that's the problem.
Wha‐What the hell
are you saying?
Jack brought his victims
closer to his idea
of perfection by
removing their genitals,
and he tried to do the same for
himself by keeping the parts
of them that he lacked.
So what does it mean
if he only kept
the female sex organs
and left the male ones behind?
[gasps] He didn't need the dicks
'cause he's already got one!
Right. Our perpetrator
is someone
with male sex organs,
and on top of that,
they're able to get Kyogoku
to do their bidding.
Here's the lesson:
What does a cheating
husband have in common
with an ambitious angel?
I bet you're gonna tell me!
Both of them are about
to suffer a nasty fall.
The true identity
of Jack the Ripper...
[SHERLOCK]
...is Maki Hokari.
Ah. You two...
I'm so glad you're here!
I think someone's
been following me.
Can you help me?
You are Jack the Ripper.
[gasps] Wait...
What are you trying to say?
I don't... understand. Ah...
Have I done something wrong?
Please. Just stop it.
Irene stole this ridiculous
USB drive from Mayor Moran.
That's what kicked
the whole thing off.
As for what he was hiding,
my money is on
an assassination contract.
[MAKI]
Moran?
You think I have something
to do with the ward mayor?
I don't understand.
Please, I think there's‐‐
[SHERLOCK] Why take a job
from somebody like him?
[MAKI]
Please stop! You're scaring me!
All I want...
All I want is to live my life!
Once the password
on this drive is cracked,
everything comes out,
which is why you would do
anything to get it back.
But you panicked
and started getting sloppy.
Stop it! You're so cruel...
I've never hurt anyone, so why
are you saying these things?
Here's the glass
you were drinking from
at the Pipe Cat, and here's
the peyote Kyogoku
was dosed with when
he attacked Watson.
If we were to dust them
for prints right now,
I'm quite sure we'd
find yours all over both.
You tricked him
into taking the drugs,
probably told him it
was an aphrodisiac.
Added a load of psychedelics
to the stress of
his first sexual experience
to get him good and paranoid.
And of course, pure as he was,
Kyogoku held onto the pills as
a memento from his first night
with the woman he loved.
[MAKI sobbing]
[retches]
[masculine voice]
Just thinking of that cretin
makes me wanna throw up!
[gasps]
[feminine voice]
Look at that‐‐You ruined it.
Now I have to redo
my whole face...
You could keep
working on it all night,
but there's no covering
up the ugliness inside.
The cowardice that still
won't let you admit defeat.
The envy that drove you to kill.
Murdering beautiful people,
carving out their sex organs,
and turning them into angels
in a show of your
hideous idea of beauty.
Pfft. Like some wannabe god.
You know it can't
change what you are.
A petty, spiteful,
ugly human with a dick
the size of a grubworm.
[MAKI humming]
Just shut up.
[whimpers]
[voice cracking] Don't start
talking like you know me.
Oh, I don't.
But I do know
a little bit about you.
You've got issues you're
not strong enough to face.
So you make yourself
out as a divine being,
and use that to justify your
murderous temper tantrums.
There is one thing that I
can't make sense of, though.
You hate that sad,
little prick of yours,
and you should have plenty
of blood money saved up.
You scared of surgery, too?
[MAKI snarls]
[screams]
[WATSON gasps]
[MAKI (masculine voice)]
I'm scared of nothing!
I am perfect!
I don't need surgery!
Why cut off my dick
when I can cut off yours?!
And your ears,
your eyes, your fingers‐‐
They're gonna be picking up
pieces of you for years!
[SHERLOCK]
Thanks for telling me.
[MAKI gasps]
[recording] Why cut off my dick
when I can cut off yours?!
And your ears,
your eyes, your fingers.
They're gonna be picking up
pieces of you for years!
[MAKI whimpers]
[sighs]
Doesn't matter.
The game's already over.
Hah... But how I wish
I could have cut up
that pretty little Moriarty‐‐
‐‐[bones cracking]
‐‐[MAKI screams]
[wailing]
Well, isn't that a shame.
That pretty little boy got away.
Moriarty!
[MAKI whimpering]
Why did you kill my sister?
[MAKI whimpers] She was
the most beautiful creature
I ever laid eyes on.
Perfect in every way...
Her hair as fine as silk...
That alabaster skin‐‐oh, God.
In the end,
when I opened her up...
‐‐[MORIARTY snarls]
‐‐[MAKI grunts]
‐‐[blood splattering]
‐‐[MAKI whimpering]
[WATSON groans]
[whimpering continues]
[MAKI] You're so beautiful
when you're mad...
It makes my heart pound,
like I'm back with her...
Feeling her life drain out...
It wasn't a coincidence.
You had a target that night.
And the drive...
My father had all the info he
would need to put you away.
That garbage‐eating fuck up
in the raincoat called it
before you got here.
Mayor Moran hired me to do it.
I honestly wasn't in much of
a killing mood at that point,
but at the end of the day,
a man has to eat,
and I could never walk away
from a paycheck like that.
[MORIARTY] But... Dad would
have no reason to take out
a hit on Alex!
[laughs]
Yeah, you're right.
Alex wasn't the one
your father paid me to kill.
[MORIARTY gasps]
Shut up... It's not true!
I assure you it is.
'Cause the real target's name
is also the password
to that USB drive.
‐‐It's you, Moriarty!
‐‐[MORIARTY gasps]
Thing is, the mayor
didn't warn me
that I might run into somebody
else wearing your clothes.
I had nothing to go on
but a transmitter signal.
I only followed the plan.
How could I have known
it was pointing me
to sweet little Alex?
And that transmitter
is the reason you had
to leave your life on
the West Side behind...
[SHERLOCK] ...when you
found it on her corpse.
[WATSON] Then the person
trying to kill me was‐‐
Moran.
He knew about his
son's trips to the East Side
and he needed to
put a stop to it.
Hence the password:
Moriarty.
[MAKI giggles]
Bingo!
But Alex was
exactly the type I like,
so I was still grateful
for the opportu‐‐
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
[MAKI whimpers]
Would you like to know...
...what she said
while she was dying?
What did she say? Tell me!
[MAKI laughing]
O‐Ooh!
Enough! Don't do it.
Stop this. You're not a killer.
‐‐[MORIARTY] Stay back!
‐‐[SHERLOCK gasps]
Tell me. What did Alex say?!
[ALEX gasps]
[MAKI panting]
[ALEX whimpers]
[MAKI giggling]
[ALEX gasps]
‐‐[MAKI snarling, laughing]
‐‐[ALEX yelps]
[laughing continues]
[inaudible]
[MAKI (feminine voice)]
"James. I will always love you.
So whatever happens,
promise you won't give up
on loving this world."
[masculine voice]
That was it.
Don't you see?
Alex was happy to die.
She was ready to give up
her life in your place! Heh!
[MORIARTY snarls]
[MARY panting]
Guys! What's happening here?!
Hey. Put down the knife!
One more thing:
Would you like to know what
I did with Alex's womb?
And all the others?
[giggles]
Stop! You can't!
[moans] I had to make them all
part of me, and Alex's tasted‐‐
[MAKI groans]
[body thuds]
Please, Sherlock.
Give it to me.
Please, Sherlock Holmes.
[SHERLOCK sighs]
[CATS meowing]