[TEACHER 05A]
We have a transfer student
joining us today.
Go ahead and introduce yourself.
I'm Minori Asagiri.
Nice to meet you.
[school bell rings]
[STUDENT 05AA] For real?
Your dad runs a company? No way!
[STUDENT 05BB]
That's awesome!
Wanna see the mansion?
I sure do!
[STUDENT 05A] Why don't we
make it a welcoming party?!
[STUDENT 05BB]
Sounds like a plan!
Whoever's going,
write your name down.
[STUDENT 05A]
You got it!
[STUDENT 05B]
There we go! See you there!
[STUDENT 05C]
Should we ask Kageyama?
[STUDENT 05A]
What do you think?
[STUDENTS laugh]
So, what's his story?
Token loser?
[STUDENT 05AA]
Who knows?
I've never really
thought about him.
[STUDENT 05BB]
Yeah, he's barely noticeable.
[MINORI]
Hm...
Is that so?
[MOGAMI]
Everybody here is an accurate
representation of actual
people from the real world.
So what you're experiencing
is a parallel world
that could've easily
come to pass had
your circumstances
been slightly different.
I'll just sit back and
observe how you fare
in this environment
without your powers.
[slap]
[TEACHER 05A]
You don't know, huh?
Don't give me that!
Are my lessons that
boring for you?
You can remain standing.
[STUDENT 05D] All that was left
was the basic addition.
[STUDENT 05E]
Talk about lame.
[STUDENT 05G]
Cut it out, guys.
[STUDENT 05H]
He's completely frozen.
[MOGAMI] You had many
relationships in real life,
and you were fortunate enough
to be surrounded by good people.
But situations like
that are rare.
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A]
No phone, no wallet,
and no parents at home, huh?
Don't give me that crap!
How about I break your nose?!
[MOB]
Please. Just let me go.
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A]
What's that? You wanna go?
Bring it, you little baby!
Come on, fight me!
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03B]
Kick his ass!
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A] What the
hell are you looking at?!
[MOGAMI]
Your extremely talented brother
is just a stranger here.
I've noticed that
you tend to refrain
from using your powers
in your personal life.
I assume you're trying to become
a better person by focusing
on your social skills
rather than your abilities.
How very noble of you.
But only the fortunate in life
would even have that idea.
Shows how lightly
you take the real world.
It'd be so much easier
if I were stronger.
Here, got some milk for you!
Wait, I thought I heard you
say that you loved milk.
Isn't this what you meant?
Ew. You totally reek.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[TEACHER 05A]
All right, settle down.
And one of you
better mop that up.
[MOGAMI] I'm sure this seems
incomprehensible to you,
but she's bullying you to secure
her position in society.
It's something she and
many people do routinely.
If you don't become stronger,
you'll be used, exploited,
and will forever be
a stepping stone for others.
[DIMPLE]
Not looking good.
Pretty sure Shigeo lost.
[REIGEN] But, it hasn't
even been 30 minutes yet.
[DIMPLE]
That's way too long!
He should've been
completely done
in less than a minute.
'Cause if this keeps up,
he'll lose his sense of self.
And he's gonna die!
Mob is someone who has a knack
for solving things on his own.
Unlike me, he's actually
pretty strong and capable.
[DIMPLE]
Quit being naive.
The next time this guy wakes up,
he's gonna wipe
the floor with us.
[MOGAMI]
Anxiety, fear, rage...
All the negative emotions
are welling up inside you.
But after living in this
world for six months
without your powers,
I'd say that's only natural.
You kept telling
yourself you mustn't
misuse your abilities.
I could see spirits since
the day I was born.
I even had the power
to exorcise them.
At first, I used my
abilities for good.
Giving advice and
solving various problems.
But my mother developed
a mysterious illness,
and the fees for her treatment
were beyond obscene.
Eventually, I started
taking underground jobs
to make ends meet.
And I killed people for money.
I even gave up sleep to
earn as much as I could.
[MOGAMI] Despite all that,
my mother still died.
The cause remained
unclear to the end.
And there was nothing
anyone could do.
But then, I found out the truth.
After her death,
my mother became
an evil spirit and said...
[MOGAMI'S MOM]
You did this to me.
It's all your fault!
[MOGAMI] The deeds I committed
to help pay the bills
brought evil around me,
and that's what
ended up plaguing her.
I should've doubted
my way of life,
how I was being used by others.
Early yesterday, Keiji Mogami...
[MOGAMI] After my demise,
I became an evil spirit
and decided to use my powers
for myself this time...
...and change the world.
I sought out those
who brought misery
and misfortune to others...
and punished them.
By dwelling inside that girl,
I knew I would be able
to take down a number
of these self-proclaimed
psychics, as well.
These acts of justice
are how I chose
to use my abilities.
You are allowed to use
your powers for yourself.
You should use
them for yourself.
You understand that
now, don't you?
[MOB]
Here you go.
[MINORI]
So what the hell are you doing?
Don't you know
that feeding strays
is a disservice to the public?
What are you gonna do about it?
[MOB]
N-Nothing, I guess.
Really? That poor thing.
In that case,
the cat's probably
better off dead than alive.
I'll just drop it
off at a shelter.
[MOB]
Don't...
--Quit scaring Minori, you punk!
--[MOB] I'll keep it!
[STUDENT 05I]
You hear me?
[MOB, STUDENT 05I grunting]
Holy crap, the door
just broke open!
But it was sealed up
so tightly a minute ago.
The reason it worked
out is because
he's not concentrating as
much of his power out here.
Now we can all
make a run for it!
[MAN 05A]
Call an ambulance!
[MAN 05B]
Help carry the wounded!
You're not staying here?
Shigeo's done for.
You gotta accept that.
Why not run away?
Because I still
have faith in him.
In this situation?
You're not really
that stupid, are ya?
Yup, actually, I am.
Let me guess:
this is the first time
someone's placed so much
trust in you, too, right?
U-Uh...
Mob only trusts us
because he's stupid.
See how that works?
I've still got plenty
of use for him.
And considering
that, running away
is the last thing I wanna do.
[groans]
[DIMPLE] Well, I can't
bring out Shigeo's
latent powers on my own.
And since that's
not going to change,
it'd be more effective
to manipulate him
from the shadows.
Okay, I changed my mind.
I'm staying behind, as well.
Good. Let's wait this out.
[DIMPLE] Oh, no. Waiting's
not gonna bring him back.
Guess I'll have to find a way
to take care of this one myself.
[MOGAMI]
Are you frustrated? Enraged?
Do you hate them?
Do you despise them?
They are a cancer to society.
Stop letting them use you
however they choose.
Let yourself be reborn
as my sympathizer.
I shall give you strength,
make your negative
emotions explode
and then use them against
the entire world!
[DIMPLE grunting]
I'm having a hard
time getting in!
Shigeo actually got through
this shield? Damn it!
Whoa! Feels like my spiritual
power is suddenly spiking.
That should do the trick!
What do you know?
Looks like it worked.
[MATSUO]
You owe me one.
Now that I've helped you,
you'd better win this.
Wh-What's with you
all of the sudden?
Y-You better stay away from me!
Or I'll have Papa's bodyguards
beat the crap out of you!
[MOB]
I doubt it.
[whimpers]
[MOB]
Apologize.
[MOGAMI]
Yes! Make her disappear!
Apologize.
[gasps]
I-I'm sorry.
If you ever bother me
again, you'll regret it.
[STUDENT 05I]
Just die, you freak!
[gasps]
Yeah, that's right,
you should just die.
[MOB]
What did I ever do to you?
To any of you?
I can't think of anything.
Either way, it doesn't matter.
None of this matters.
[MOGAMI] There. It's complete.
You finally changed.
You were a lot like me...
...and that's why I didn't
want you to travel
the same path I did.
Yo.
[MOB]
The snot's talking to me!
[DIMPLE] Whoa, you're pretty
far gone, aren't ya?
Hey! Do you know who I am?
[MOB]
What the heck is this thing?
[DIMPLE]
Actually, before that...
Ah-ha!
[MOGAMI grunts]
Quit your spying!
[DIMPLE] Damn you for actually
falling for these illusions.
[DIMPLE]
Fine.
I'll have to use all
the spiritual power
I've stocked up, but...
Time for shock therapy!
[MOB grunts]
Get it together, Shigeo!
Reigen and I are waiting
for you outside!
Wait, what? Who's Reigen?
[phone rings]
[REIGEN]
Oh, hey, Mob.
Sorry, but could you
hurry to the office?
A huge job just came in.
Your master needs your help,
so uh, shake a leg.
Mas... ter...?
Stop using your powers
for dumb things
in this made-up world.
Don't you wanna
be an inspiration
for your little brother?
I have a little...
...brother?
[gasps]
[MOB] I wore the wrong
shoes. These are Ritsu's.
[DIMPLE] Don't let Mogami
mess with your head like that.
You've always stuck
to your values,
even when you fought Hanazawa!
That's right...
I shouldn't use these powers
against other people.
On top of that,
why are you losing
to a bunch of
common street thugs?
Aren't you in the
Body Improvement Club?
What happened to
all those muscles
you've been building up?
Look, I don't know how much time
you've spent in this lousy
excuse for a world,
but this isn't like you.
Do you want your beloved
Tsubomi to hate your guts?
[gasps]
Well done, kid.
--Hey, bro!
--[TERU] 'Sup?
[GODA]
Body improvement...
[ALL]
Fight on!
[DIMPLE]
Now that's a bit much.
Uh...
[MOB]
I remember now.
[DIMPLE] Hm?! Then you
remember me too, doncha?
We're partners!
No, doesn't really ring a bell.
[DIMPLE]
Aw, seriously?
I'm only kidding.
Thanks, Dimple. You saved me.
[MOGAMI] It doesn't
matter if your memories
returned to you or not.
The six months
you've spent here
are forever etched into
your heart and mind.
I know you were hearing
my voice subconsciously.
Mogami...
[MOB] Yeah. And it's
just like you said.
The world can be a cruel
and messed-up place.
You helped me
see it in a new light.
[DIMPLE]
Huh? Wait. Don't tell me you...?
I'm surrounded by good people.
I need to be more
thankful for them...
...once I'm back
in the real world.
So that's how it's
going to be, huh?
And here I thought I'd
found a kindred spirit.
How disappointing.
[MOB]
One other thing.
When you interact
with other people,
it can have an effect.
And because of that,
I was able to change.
Thanks to them, I'm stronger.
Much stronger than
if I'd been on my own
If I'm able to change,
then anyone should be able to.
We can lift each other up.
No one is worthless.
[MOGAMI] That's enough.
Don't say another word.
If you do, there'll
be hell to pay.
[MOB] The Shigeo you
created in this world
might give into you,
but I won't.
I'm not running.
I've got a job to do.
I still have to save
that awful Minori.
[DIMPLE]
A spiritual mutation?
Guess we're gonna have to fight!
You up for this, Shigeo?
Suppose I'll take
that as a "yes."
[gasps]
[DIMPLE]
Here come some more!
Every being in this world is...
[EVIL SPIRITS moaning]
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo!
[gasps]
[MOB]
That's...
[MOB grunts]
[MOB] I'm going to defeat
this evil spirit
and go back to reality.
[MOGAMI]
And what good would that do?
Your life won't change,
nor will the
absurdity of society.
There will always be
plenty of things
in the world to bring you down.
[MOB]
The outside world is... scary?
[MOGAMI] Yes. Life is
frustrating, devoid of meaning,
and so, so painful.
I can hear them.
[MOB]
The voices of the dead...
They're speaking to me.
So many screams...
They died feeling like this?
Is this how they felt
when they were alive?
The world can be
such a cruel place.
Am I really going
to be able to--
--[MINORI] Please...
--[gasps]
[MOB]
That voice!
[MINORI]
Please, help me...
[MOB]
Wait... That's right.
I remember now. I came
here to save someone.
[MOB] I always thought
these powers were trivial.
That they were no
good to anybody.
But I can use them
to save people!
It doesn't matter what you do.
You can never defeat me!
[DIMPLE]
Well, I'll be damned. Shigeo...
You did it!
[MOGAMI] You're not the
same boy from earlier.
Tell me. Who are you?
Now you're gonna find
out just how strong
this kid really is!
You're looking at the
freaky-but-true form
he reveals when
he's super pissed!
You're in for it n--!
[MOB]
Dimple.
It's dangerous, so stay back...
...and leave this to me.
[DIMPLE]
He really has changed, huh?
[NARRATOR]
Mogami had made the mistake
of overlooking something
that lay dormant within Mob.
Hearts are made up of two sides.
Just as happiness gleams
in the shadows of sorrow...
...only in the darkest
depths of fear
does courage truly shine.
[NARRATOR] The powerful
blast created from Mob's
positive emotions
at 100 percent
annihilated the great
and powerful
evil spirit, Mogami.
Or at least, that's
how it looked...
[MOGAMI] Now that they've
lost me, their vessel,
all of the evil spirits
I'd taken in and controlled
will be freed into the
universe. Good luck.
Not even I can
stop them anymore.
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo!
Dimple! Get out of here!
I'm gonna be all right!
Just leave me!
Really? You sure about that?!
[MOB yelling]
[MOB]
I'm going to save Minori...
...and exorcise these
guys before I go.
I'll be back,
I promise. Don't worry.
[DIMPLE]
Hm.
Hmph!
You wanna eat me, too?
Fine! Catch me if
you can, ya bastards!
Bring it!
[DIMPLE]
See you on the other side!
[MOB]
In this world...
...everything I can
see is a spirit.
[MOB]
And I have to cast them all out.
[MOGAMI]
No matter how much you struggle,
your path will lead you
to the same place mine did.
To ruin.
[MOB grunts]
[MOB gasps]
[gasps]
[MOB]
No, I still have to save her...
Wait!
[MOB]
It can't end like this!
[MOGAMI]
Ah, I see.
Once your vessel has been
completely shattered...
...that is what remains?
[MOB gasps]
I almost thought you were dead.
Man, that took you ages.
Yes, it did.
Master, how's Minori?
Well, if you're
awake, then maybe...
[MOB]
He's still--!
[MOGAMI]
You've made your choice, kid.
I'll keep watching
from afar to see
if you made the right one.
[MATSUO] You're not going
anywhere, my pet.
What an unexpected trophy.
You have my thanks.
[REIGEN]
Isn't that...?
Huh, I didn't even
realize he was here.
[MATSUO] I'll be sure to take
really good care of him.
Perhaps we'll see each other
again sometime. Farewell.
[MINORI grunts]
Kageyama. You're here?
Yeah.
[REIGEN] Hold up.
You guys know each other?
[DIMPLE] Nah, she
probably just remembers
what happened over there.
Are you really always like that?
In real life, I mean.
Uh-- Yeah. Actually, I am.
Sorry.
[MINORI sobs]
I'm sorry. Really sorry.
I was so awful! I'm so sorry!
[MOB]
It's okay. I know.
Know what?
That people are able to change.
Mogami and Minori both taught
me that it's possible.
The people around me
changed me, as well.
Now I understand that I can do
the same thing for others, too.
So, I get it.
And I'm glad we
were able to meet.
[gasps]
Thank you so much.
[ASAGIRI]
So what you're saying is:
the one who saved you was a boy
in the same grade as you?
Yeah, why do you ask?
[ASAGIRI] Well, there
wasn't a middle school
student among the
people that I hired.
[MINORI]
Huh?
He wasn't even
asked to be there,
but somehow he
managed to cast out
an evil spirit that
nobody else could,
and then left without
saying a word.
That's so cool.
I hope I can see him again.
I've been digging around online,
and after a bit of research,
this caught my eye.
Hey. Isn't that...?
[BELIEVER 05A]
Our religious organization
won't survive on
donations alone.
It's gonna be impossible
to build a headquarters.
[BELIEVER 05B]
And our beloved leader
is still nowhere to be found.
[BELIEVER 05C]
Hm.
[MOB]
I don't get it, Master.
Why aren't you
claiming your reward?
Just look at how
many people got hurt.
Not exactly a big success.
[REIGEN]
You should never accept money
that you feel you
haven't earned.
If you do, you'll start taking
the easy way out every time.
You just don't wanna be
held responsible, huh?
That's not it, moron!
Anyway, history has shown us
that no good ever comes out
of drowning in wealth,
fame, or power.
Think about it: Mogami
let his own powers
swallow him up, too.
You know...
You're better off
working part-time for me
than becoming famous
or powerful.
I hope this serves as
a good lesson for ya.
Come on, give me
a friggin' break...
[MOB gasps]
[REIGEN]
Hey, quit clowning around
with your classmates, Mob!
We're busy here!
They're just using you, anyway!
Jeez. You never learn, do ya?
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode six:
"Poor, Lonely, Whitey."
The DVDs? That's an
excellent decision!