[gasps]
[DIMPLE] Shigeo, relax!
Just try to stay calm!
Look into my eyes, will ya?!
Listen carefully.
I can tell these aren't
real bodies, okay?
They're only dummies!
Some esper probably
put them here
to try and fool you!
Come on, Dimple.
You expect me to believe that?
Think about everything
that you've seen!
It's totally possible!
Mob, they're still out there!
I found them.
[DIMPLE]
Did he just learn a new power?
Let's get those guys!
Thank you.
You stopped me.
You brought me back.
Hey! No time for
that, we have to go
and find those guys! Don't we?
Of course.
I'm going to get all three
of them back right now.
Whoever did this is gonna pay.
It doesn't matter
how far they run.
[PUNK] Is there a point to
setting the place on fire?
Makes it obvious that the
situation has been dealt with.
[CROWD gasps]
--[GIRL 09A] What was that?
--[GUY 09A] A meteor?
[BALD]
What the hell?
[MAYUO cackles]
You must be Hanazawa.
Hanazawa?
Oh, the guy that lives downsta--
Telekinetic Explosion!
[MAYUO cackles]
[BALD]
I know you.
You're our target;
that middle-school kid.
How the hell did you
find out about us,
you little brat?
Well, whatever.
You can die here.
[CROWD gasps]
Wow! You're fairly resilient!
[BALD]
Huh?!
Where did you take my family?
Ah, tough guy, are ya?
Well, either you'll
die from my powers
of electrocution, or I'll
die trying to kill you!
Not interested.
Use something other
than electricity.
[PUNK yells]
Is this really all you can do?
You're free to go.
[yelps]
[MOB] So... maybe
you're the guy, then.
Show me your powers!
Got a bad attitude, kid.
If you're that desperate
to see my powers...
...I'll show 'em to you!
[yells]
[GUY 09B] Some old guy
and a middle school kid
are fighting!
[BALD] I have indestructible
armor made out of energy.
See? I put that up and beat
the crap out of my enemies.
It's kinda my thing.
Seriously...
Could you guys quit
wasting my time?
Looks like you've got
a decent barrier, too.
Is that your power, kid--
[MOB]
That's enough!
[MOB] Show me the power that
creates those dummies!
Do it! Show me!
Why did you bastards
attack my house?!
[GUY 09C]
Somebody, call the police!
You've got the wrong
idea about us...
We were on our way
to attack your house.
We hadn't done anything yet...
What did you say?! Hey!
Nobody said you could
pass out! Talk to me!
Damn it...
[PUNK laughs]
I spoke to the upper echelon.
You're totally screwed now.
Say your prayers, kid.
This isn't good.
That means there are more
espers headed this way.
I think we should...
These two had no information
on what happened.
If they have more
friends coming,
I'll just ask them, instead.
[DIMPLE]
Hm...
An umbrella?
--[car horn blares]
--[GUY 09D] Whoa!
[GUY 09E yelps]
Hey, you little punk.
Are you in trouble?
[KOYAMA]
Ease off the murder-vibe.
Nobody here's trying to
start anything with you.
Right?
Listen...
If you've got
questions, just ask.
I assume you're
taking me wherever
my family is, correct?
What, your family? Sorry, no.
Then I have no reason
to go. Let me out.
Wait! Your family's not there,
but your friends and master are!
Reigen's there?
Why didn't you say so?
We need to hurry!
[KOYAMA]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute!
Take it easy! Stop!
[KOYAMA]
Ugh, I'm gonna throw up...
[SAKURAI] At least we
know no one followed us.
[KOYAMA]
Hey. We got him here.
Shigeo Kageyama.
Long time no see, kid.
I trust you haven't
let yourself go.
I know when we last
met, we were rivals.
But I look forward
to working with you.
What the--?! What kind
of group is this?
Mob, you all right?
Master...
My home is...
My family...
[REIGEN]
Sit down. Talk to me.
Let him rest.
I can fill you in on
everything that happened.
I see.
Dimple. A word, please?
Sure.
[REIGEN]
Did you just freak out and lie
about the dummies?
[DIMPLE] Kinda, but I do
have reasons to believe it.
[REIGEN] Man, you must've
really been panicking.
If Mob finds out you lied,
he's gonna hate you forever.
Hey, Mob. We need to talk.
Hang on, are you
gonna tell him?!
'Cause if he finds out
the truth, then he might--
[REIGEN]
Mob. About what Dimple said...
I think your family
is safe, too.
[gasps]
Those esper guys were
still on their way
to your house, right?
Someone must've
found out they were
in danger and rushed
over to save them.
They started the
fire and made them
look dead so they wouldn't
be targeted anymore.
Isn't that great?
The moment he relaxed,
he fell fast asleep.
Now it's your turn to
tell me what's goin' on.
What the hell brought this
group together, anyway?
Aren't these guys from Claw?!
We're all former members
of the 7th Division of Claw,
to be precise about it.
After being annihilated by
a group of middle school kids,
we realized just how
foolish we all were.
[MURAKI] And now, we're all
trying to put those days
behind us and begin a new life.
Just like Master Reigen does,
we're trying to find
ways to use our powers
for the good of society.
But the organization doesn't
let traitors walk away.
[SAKURAI] We knew they'd come
after us sooner or later,
but this was a lot faster
than we anticipated.
They launched
coordinated attacks
on all of us simultaneously.
I'm just impressed you survived.
Who do you think we are?
We're former Scars,
so we can handle it.
Right, Tsucchi?
Yeah.
But the real battle begins
when the guys from HQ show up.
After that, we realized
if we're going
to stand a chance against them,
we need to make sure
we have a good leader.
Smart choice.
And naturally, that led
them to my door.
Shut up. It's better that way.
When Master Reigen put the TV
and media people in their place,
we thought it was a genius move.
He sees the bigger picture
and makes things happen.
The exact qualities
we're looking for.
[DIMPLE] Are they serious?
Talk about misguided.
Wait, didn't Claw
come after you, too?
Yeah, my office was destroyed.
Fortunately for me,
I just happened to be away
the moment it was incinerated.
With the flood of new clients
my TV appearance brought me,
I thought I'd invest
in some renovations.
That's my office, by the
sign on the building.
The one that's... burning...
[REIGEN] So, those renovations
will have to wait.
After that, the former
Claw guys picked me up.
I was already exhausted
from the marathon.
Man, talk about a crappy day.
Huh. Makes me wonder
if Teru's doing okay.
Oh! I got a message
from him earlier.
He said he's just fine.
[ASAHI]
When did that happen?
[ASAHI, HOSHINO]
This sucks.
So, what are you
guys doing here?
After what happened
with the 7th Division,
we're trying to lay low.
Mitsuura called and
said he'd prepared
this hideout for us.
I can't believe there
are so many espers
in one spot! This is
so freakin' cool!
Oh, him.
[ALL gasp]
[HOSHINO, ASAHI]
Teru!
Hey. Well, it looks like
the gang's all here.
[MAYUO]
You fools!
If you punks think
you can make me talk,
then you're dead wrong,
you understand me?!
I'm a member of Cla--!
[MAYUO yelps]
[TERADA]
Is that so?
Stop resisting, nobody
can endure this torture.
[MAYUO gasps]
Sorry! I'll talk!
The boss has been
going around the world
scouting powerful espers
until the other day
when he said that he finally had
all of the soldiers he needed!
I see.
Gathering espers from
around the world, huh?
[MAYUO] Don't tell me you idiots
still plan on facing us
after hearing that!
We've got an army of powerful--
Master Reigen.
What should we do now?
Hmph!
There's no way we're just
gonna let this slide.
Let's report them to the police.
[gasps]
[JOSEPH]
Amazing isn't it?
This whole civilization was
built by ordinary humans.
I'm so excited. I can't
wait to destroy it.
That is why we came to
this country, isn't it?
Not me.
I came for the money.
[BOSS]
Ladies and gentlemen...
Thank you all for gathering
on this historic day.
For those of you
who don't know,
I'm Toichiro Suzuki,
the leader of Claw.
The time is finally upon us.
We are about to declare
war on the entire world.
After 20 years, I finally have
the funds and manpower
needed to wage this battle.
Our revolution will
begin with destruction.
The annihilation of
everything that people
built and hold dear.
Let us show the
powerless that our kind
will no longer hide
in the shadows!
[CLAW MEMBERS cheer]
Huh. World Domination.
Seems pretty ambitious to me
Are the preparations complete?
There's nothing
I need to prepare.
[MEMBER 09A]
What are they doing?
[MEMBER 09B]
Is that a camera?
You're now live
on every channel.
[NARRATOR] Hatori's
psychic ability allows him
to infiltrate and
control systems dealing
with electronic
devices or waves.
And he has no idea
how it actually works.
Wow. He's good.
[BOSS]
Attention.
We are an organization
of espers known as Claw.
We've taken over the airwaves
with our psychic powers.
And that is but
a single fraction
of what we are truly capable of.
Our abilities are far superior
to all modern weaponry.
I warn you: it's not
advisable to oppose us.
We will soon control
the world using
our psychic powers
and begin ruling over
you defenseless humans.
The first step in our
mission is to completely
demolish this country.
A new world order
is about to begin.
I look forward to ruling you.
[SHO pants]
I can't believe it.
How dare you...
...embarrass your own
son like this again?!
I will be the one
to defeat him!
Got that, Ritsu?!
Got it.
All right! Let's go!
Hang on a second.
[SHO] You're still not
on board with this?
What's the hold up?
What about my family's safety?
Oh. Don't worry about
a thing, 'cause we have
somebody keeping a close
eye on your parents
from a distance.
See? They're fine.
We told your mom
and dad that you
wanted to do something
nice for them...
...so you entered a hot springs
hotel lottery and won!
And they totally fell for it!
[RITSU] You were really
pushing it with a lie that big.
Their hotel doesn't have ties
to anything shady, does it?
[SHO]
Hey, don't worry.
They offer traditional
seafood, farm-fresh meals,
and accommodate allergies, too.
It's pretty posh.
That's not what
I'm talking about!
And what about my brother?
He's still not
answering his phone.
I'm sure he's safe.
But he won't fight.
I could see it in his eyes.
He's not the type to blow up
without a really good reason.
I think I gave him a
pretty good one, though.
[RITSU]
What do you mean?
Did you do something
after we left the house?
Listen, if you did
anything that might've
pissed my brother off...
...then you're in big trouble.
Heh.
Sounds like you've had
a pretty hard life too, then.
Let me explain that plan
the boss was talking about.
In Japan, the total
number of policemen
and military personnel
who have guns
is roughly 600,000.
[BOSS] As of this moment,
the number of agents
in Claw stands around 600.
Each one of you will
have to face about
1,000 armed opponents in battle.
That shouldn't be a problem.
[CRAW MEMBERS murmur]
[MEMBER 09C] How awesome!
That's our boss for ya!
[MEMBER 09D]
Who knew it'd be so easy?
[MEMBER 09E] This actually seems
possible all of a sudden.
[LONG HAIR] Can you really
even call that a plan?
[JOSEPH] Doesn't seem
likely to work, does it?
They're hopeless,
how disappointing.
[LONG HAIR] What are ya
thinking, Joseph? Tell us.
[JOSEPH]
Probably the same as you guys.
According to his logic,
if each one of us
defeats about 120 people...
...we can destroy Claw.
We're gonna start a mutiny?
That sounds like way more fun!
Yeah! I don't care what we do
as long as I can break stuff!
[JOSEPH] First, we need
to make an example
of the upper echelon.
[TAMAKI]
What?
You wanna destroy
the organization?
You're gonna give
up future glory
for the sake of money?
What vile creatures you are.
I'll take care of you myself.
Come at me, cowards!
[gasps]
[laughs]
I'm gonna punch you.
Hope you can put up a barrier.
[JOSEPH] Claw's a dangerous
esper organization, huh?
For a plot 20 years
in the making,
it sure is full of holes.
[BOSS] An elephant that's
about to crush 1,000 ants
has little to worry about.
Wouldn't you agree?
[chuckles]
I'm really starting
to feel sorry for you.
You have no idea the
Japanese government's
already watching you,
nor who it is
that you're talking to.
So, were you the only spy
here sent by the government?
Afraid so.
But I found some others
with a taste for treason.
This organization will
implode before your plan...
...can even begin.
--So...
--[JOSEPH gasps]
[SERIZAWA]
President Suzuki took you in,
but you were lying to him?!
How could you do
something so awful?!
[JOSEPH]
White Noise!
[SERIZAWA]
Whoa!
Impressive work.
Must be hard to
move around in that.
[JOSEPH]
Hmph!
Once it hardens, it's
as strong as steel.
Anyone who gets caught in it--
[gasps]
[JOSEPH]
Miguel!
--[BOSS] You said...
--[gasps]
...you felt sorry for me
a moment ago, didn't you?
But now, I feel sorry for you .
[MINEGISHI]
No more extra work, okay?
I have enough to do as it is.
[SHIBATA] Well, well,
what a pathetic sight.
These guys are supposed to be
in our upper eshelon.
And look at them now.
[yells]
[laughs] Seems we're
the same type.
[gasping]
The loss of my
division leaders won't
be enough of a setback
for Claw to implode.
I've dubbed Claw's main
force the Ultimate 5.
As long as they're with me...
...Claw is invincible.
This isn't over!
I can at least take you out!
What the hell?!
[yells]
[BOSS]
Well done!
I knew it'd be a waste of
your talents to continue
letting you be a shut-in.
Thanks! I re-entered society
because of you, sir!
Couldn't have done
it without you!
So where's Shimazaki?
Haven't seen him in a while.
On an errand.
He's tending to
another matter, now.
[JOSEPH panting]
[JOSEPH]
Damn them.
They're a bigger threat
than we thought.
[MITSUURA]
This meal was prepared
by the best chefs around!
Please, eat as much
as you'd like!
I'm surprised that HQ
hasn't attacked yet.
I mean, we could strike first.
But considering our numbers...
Well, Kageyama and I equal
at least 1,000 people.
That may be true,
but nothing's starts
till the kid wakes up.
Stop eating all the
roast beef, mohawk!
There's a limit!
Only three slices per person!
[KOYAMA]
Huh?
Koyama, apologize
to Master Reigen!
Lay the hell off me!
[NARRATOR] They didn't see
Claw's message on television.
[PRIME MINISTER]
In conclusion...
...by providing
opportunities to start
their own businesses,
and expanding the range
of childcare benefits beyond
the current national standard...
[SPs groan]
[PRIME MINISTER]
...we can empower the women
in our workforce with
the tools they--
Huh?
Greetings, Prime Minister.
I represent Claw,
the organization
who declared they'd
be taking over
the world last night.
You're in luck!
Because today, I've come
here to abduct you.
[gasps]
[AUDIENCE gasps]
Prime Minister! Take cover!
--[SP 08F] You're under arrest!
--[SHIMAZAKI laughs]
[SHIMAZAKI] By the way, are you
broadcasting this on TV?
It'd be awesome
for this to end up
as a breaking news story.
Shut up!
Now, freeze! Ya hear me?!
[SP 08E]
Does he have a gun?
Put him down!
Whoops, you missed.
[gasps]
--[gunshots]
--[AUDIENCE yelling]
[SHIMAZAKI]
The thing is...
...even though I can't see,
I can predict people's
movements and actions.
But even if I'm hit, I have
nothing to worry about.
See?
[SP 08I]
No way!
[SHIMAZAKI] Oh! Prime Minister!
Allow me to fill you in
on what my other
special power is.
Check it out.
[SHIMAZAKI]
I can teleport, too.
[PRIME MINISTER whimpers]
What's the meaning of this?
What is it you hope to
achieve by kidnapping me?
You're only a
hostage, that's all.
Is Claw serious about this
"world domination" crap?
[SHIMAZAKI]
Oh, yeah. Very much so.
[PRIME MINISTER yelps]
That was sneaky. Who are you?
[TERUKI]
Someone who saw the broadcast
and rushed here, then I
sensed you two in this park.
If you think everything
in life goes exactly
the way you planned it...
...then let me teach you
a lesson by taking you down.
What an odd reply
to my question.
Whatever. Give it
a shot, if you like.
[TERUKI]
Telekinetic Explosion!
Air Whips!
[TERUKI]
Where'd he go?
What? I was too careless!
[TERUKI]
Pyrokinesis!
I lost sight of him again.
Is this guy's power...?
Looking for me?
[yelps]
[pants]
[TERUKI]
Super speed movement?
In that case...
Multi-Layer Barrier!
[TERUKI] My new technique where
I overlap multiple barriers...
It should be enough
to hold him off
until the others get here.
[SHIMAZAKI]
Aren't you multi-talented?
[TERUKI gasps]
[TERUKI]
He's that quick?
Thanks for entertaining me.
[TERUKI groans]
[SAKURAI]
Hanazawa! Hey! Wake up!
[KOYAMA] Why the hell'd
you run off on your own?!
[REIGEN] The Ultimate 5 of Claw,
terrorize Seasoning City.
Meanwhile, the esper squad
and the boss's son,
Sho, make their moves.
This is no time to
be sleeping, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode ten:
"Collision ~Power Type~."
What do I recommend?
The convenient Blu-ray set
with bonus features!