[NEWSCASTER 10A] We've just
received word that Claw,
the esper terrorist
organization,
has barricaded itself inside
the Seasoning Cultural Tower.
It's possible that
Prime Minister Yabe,
who was abducted
from Pork Bone City,
is being held prisoner inside--
The PM's kidnapper
was a teleporter.
He can travel anywhere
in an instant.
[MITSUURA] And according to
what they said on the news,
he can also predict
people's movements.
Well, that's not fair at all.
How can one person have two
overpowered abilities like that?
Is that why you developed
a fever? His psychic powers?
No. Actually, it's from
the shock of losing.
I had one just like this
when I lost to Kageyama
and had nightmares for days.
This guy is bad news.
Could they have more espers
with powers like his?
I've always been
pretty confident.
Thought I could take on anyone.
But now, I don't know.
I'm not sure what to think.
[SHIMAZAKI]
I don't get it.
Why'd we move away
from the capital?
If we'd stayed, we
could've just taken over
the tallest building in Japan.
There are two reasons.
First, the rice omelets
in the cafeteria here
are to die for.
They use four large
eggs per serving.
The second reason is
because I'm from this city.
Since I know it so well,
I can easily detect any changes.
So this place is
special to you, huh?
Maybe some family and
friends who're still
living in your old neighborhood?
No, just a familiarity.
It's purely tactical.
I've no attachment.
I don't mind if you
destroy the entire city.
Yeah? Even the place
with the rice omelets?
Heh. That's correct.
[SAT TEAM 10A]
The special anti-terrorism squad
is at the Cultural Tower.
All units, prepare
to raid the building.
Should I go down there?
That won't be necessary.
Every soldier from Claw
HQ is fully capable,
I assure you.
They're only a small step below
the upper echelon: the Scars.
[gasps]
[SHIBATA]
Is that so?
Most of those guys are
artificial espers, aren't they?
When'd they become so strong?
How did they--?
They're not human!
[SHIBATA] Hey, boss.
Just out of curiosity...
Did you do something
to enhance their powers?
[HATORI] Trying to get
something for the news?
You guys are so annoying.
Just go away.
[yelps] The controls
aren't responding!
A malfunction?!
[PILOT 10A] I'm not sure!
It's gone out of control!
[laughs]
It's like an RC 'copter!
[BOSS]
Ignore all aircraft.
Hatori can handle
them on his own.
Minegishi and Shibata
will go into the town
to expand our territory.
Serizawa and Shimazaki
will defend our base.
Let's get out there
and show them all
just how powerful we are.
Go!
[KUROSAKI]
Oh, no...
I didn't know that was possible.
What can we do?
There's just so many of 'em.
Reigen, what's the plan?
Come on!
This is no time for
a cup-o-noodles break!
Now don't act like this
is outta your hands!
[REIGEN]
What are you talkin' about?
Of course, it is.
Huh?
We're not a team of superheroes,
and this stuff is dangerous.
We're better off leaving it
to the police and the JSDF.
What are you?
Some kind of chicken?
[REIGEN] No, but what
do you think we can do
against people like that?
I don't know...
We all gathered here
to ask you that,
ya noodle-munching dumbass.
[REIGEN]
Great! Then, here's my answer.
Meeting's over.
[REIGEN] I thought we might
have a chance with Mob,
but this is just too dangerous.
We'll have to lie low
until things settle down.
[TERUKI]
Reigen...
I think he's right.
That's our best option.
Well, I'm going.
I'd rather strike first
than be on the run forever.
I'm going, too!
Same here!
We have to try. This
battle is our chance
to find a purpose for ourselves.
Do whatever you want.
[phone rings]
[REIGEN] Hello? Ah, yes,
the fire insurance company!
Yes. Yes, that's right.
Huh? Wait.
If you can't figure
out the cause,
there won't be any payout?
You couldn't find
any kerosene or gas?
Of course not! It was
caused by psychic powers!
Psychic powers!
You've never dealt
with this before?
That's not my problem!
Hey, wait a sec...
My office burned to the ground!
I'm penniless!
Why the hell do I even
have insurance, then?
What are you babblin' about?
Hang on.
Look at his face.
I've never seen him so serious.
Well, crap.
You guys are determined
to fight, aren't ya?
I've changed my mind.
You want me to command you?
You've got it! Let's do this!
To victory!
[REIGEN]
And I'll find that damn arsonist
and drag them to
the insurance company!
Master Reigen's super fired up!
[REIGEN] All right.
Now that that's settled,
we need a strategy.
Everyone needs a copy
of the local map.
Apparently, the enemy is
jamming all electronic devices.
[TERUKI] Guess I was just
being too negative.
Thanks, Reigen.
[groans]
[SHO sighs]
[RITSU]
You're pretty strong.
You probably didn't even need
my help to pull this off.
Ritsu, your latent abilities
far surpass your brother's.
[RITSU]
There's no way that's true.
You're kidding, right?
Keep pushing till it is true.
You've gotta believe
in yourself.
Like me with my dad.
I'm much stronger.
[gasps]
[MINEGISHI]
Leading this little uprising
is so on-brand for you, Sho.
Talk about a textbook
rebellious phase.
This guy's aura is super weird.
Who's the plant-man?
One of the Ultimate 5,
Claw's highest echelon.
His name is Minegishi,
and he's a plant user.
If you get caught by one
of his vegetative minions,
consider yourself plant food.
He'd have the upper
hand out in a forest.
Lucky for us, this place
is a concrete jungle.
Don't worry, we'll
take care of him.
Please go on ahead, leader.
You guys...
They've got this,
Ritsu! Let's go!
[RITSU]
I have my doubts.
[CRAW MEMBER 10A]
Hey! Look up in the sky!
[CRAW MEMBER 10B]
Whoa! What's going on?
[CRAW MEMBER 10C] Are the
government's espers attacking?
Shoot 'em down!
[REIGEN] None of us
will be in those cars.
The first step in our
plan is to break up
the enemy's formation.
The goal is to try
and buy as much time
as we can before
they realize the cars
are simply decoys.
Hey, uh... Teru.
So, um, is my telekinesis
helping at all?
Yeah.
It's kinda like
somebody using their
pinky finger to try and
help carry heavy luggage.
[HOSHINO] Was it too much
to just say "not really"?
[TERUKI] Damn it. This is
too much to do alone!
[TAKEUCHI] Would you like
some help, young man?
[TERUKI]
Who are you?
[TERADA] You decided
to show up, too, huh?
My name is Takeuchi.
I am a master of the miraculous
art of super qigong.
You just need to make
some cars fly, right?
Everything above-ground
is a diversion.
We'll infiltrate their
main base through
the sewers and bring
down the boss-man.
This way.
[REIGEN]
Once they lose their leader,
none of the rest
of them should pose
any threat on their own.
[OTSUKI grunts]
[MINEGISHI]
That's no ordinary paper fan.
It's been turned into a device
that amplifies shock waves.
Quick! Everybody get
behind my shield!
[MINEGISHI]
He disassembled then reassembled
the shredded vines and leaves.
[MINEGISHI]
Interesting technique.
I can even make
a human-like doll
out of a refrigerator
as long as it has
the right parts and materials.
You feeling all right?
Better now, thanks.
[MINEGISHI] The one in the
green is a rare healing type.
They're perfectly
balanced in attack,
defense, and support.
That means it's time
for me to step up
and get serious.
Is this really the best
place for you to be?
What the hell could
I do out there?
Besides, when Mob wakes up,
it'll probably help if
he has someone familiar
here to explain
the situation to him.
But damn, is that kid
knocked out or what?
He's sleeping like
he's half dead.
I think this goes way
beyond just being tired.
Master Reigen! There's trouble!
Our security system
picked up some intruders!
[REIGEN]
Are you serious?!
It's gotta be Claw.
But how'd they find this place?
[MITSUURA] Come on!
The rear exit's this way!
[REIGEN] No, it's no good
to run off without a plan.
We need to hide!
[CRAW MEMBER 10A]
No doubt about it.
They've gotta be in there.
[CRAW MEMBER 10B] So are you
guys shaking in your boots, yet?
[CRAW MEMBER 10C]
Get your asses out here!
[DIMPLE]
What's the plan, Reigen?
Want me to possess you
so you can brawl with 'em?
[CRAW MEMBER 10A]
I'll open the door.
Stay on your guard, everyone.
[REIGEN] All right.
You got me. I give up.
I'm not an esper.
You can tell with your
tracing powers, right?
The kid on my back
actually is one,
but he hasn't been awake
since last night.
Let me just take him
to the hospital.
Seems fishy to me.
You think maybe he's
packin' a weapon?
Go frisk him and find out.
I don't have any
weapons on me, okay?
Only my phone
and a handkerchief.
He's got something
in his jacket pocket.
Oh, that. It's
just some cologne.
I work in the
fragrance industry.
Smells great, huh?
[CRAW MEMBERS groan]
[DIMPLE]
Ooh...
Apparently, it's
filled with a curse
that causes extreme drowsiness.
I grabbed it from
four-eyes a while back.
Good thing, too. It
really saved our butts.
Ah--
[SHIBATA]
Thought you were a joke,
but you're really not so bad.
Unfortunately for you,
you're gonna have
to deal with me next.
[REIGEN]
He's a big boy!
Are you ready?
[SHIBATA grunts]
[REIGEN] He's strong. But
thankfully, he's also an idiot.
I can't believe this
ridiculous lucky streak
you're on lately.
You're gonna die
a horrible death.
[BOSS] What a beautiful
sight to behold.
All that destruction...
...and yet I don't feel the
slightest tinge of remorse.
Sacrifices must be made
for world domination.
[SERIZAWA]
Is that really true?
[BOSS]
Serizawa. Why the long face?
Let me give you
a word of advice.
Oh, yes, President!
I would love to hear it!
The secret behind my
unflinching positive attitude...
...is that I've never
once concerned myself
with how others feel.
I've lived each day of my
life the way I wanted to.
As long as I can
depend on myself,
everything will always work out.
Even if I lose all
of you, I doubt
it would do anything
to break my spirit.
I've decided to
take over the world,
so that's what's
going to happen.
Since I have the
audacity to say that,
it's basically in
my hands already.
I'm sure you know
this, Serizawa,
but I think very highly
of your potential.
You held back on
Joseph, didn't you?
You need to obtain a
calm and bold positivity.
Then you can be just
like me: unstoppable.
I see!
That's how to climb
a corporate ladder?
[SHIMAZAKI] His misunderstanding
has gotten even worse.
I mean, this isn't
even a company.
What'll we do now?
They found our hideout!
First, we'll grab a taxi
and get outta here.
--[SHIBATA growls]
--[DIMPLE] Look out!
Huh? What the hell?!
I thought you were out cold!
I was! But too bad for you,
'cause I'm wide
awake now, dumbass!
Ah! That's awesome!
Look, I seriously
give up this time.
I'm a lover, not a fighter...
Idiot! Run for it, Reigen!
Oh, crap! Mob!
[SHIBATA]
Psycho Steroid!
I send psychic
signals to my muscles
and adjust them for maximum--
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Go back to sleep.
[yells]
Think that really
pissed him off.
Moron! Now he's even
more powered up!
Enough of this!
I'm gonna lure him out!
He's not coming? Mob! Wake up!
[roars]
[DIMPLE]
I panicked for a second,
but this guy's not an
evil spirit. He's human!
That means I can break him!
Okay, I was wrong.
This guy's not human at all.
Damn! This isn't good!
Catch him, Reigen!
Right! I was on the
boys' volleyball team
for about five minutes!
Bring it!
No! Dimple!
Is-Is Mob's body okay?
That was close.
But, I think he'll be fine.
Thanks to his shoe falling off.
But that did prove
one thing, for sure.
There's no way I
can win this fight!
Can't let that big lug catch me!
[SHIBATA yells]
[REIGEN]
Are they gonna be all right?
[NEWSCASTER 10B]
The terrorist organization
that has taken over
part of Seasoning City
continues to wreak havoc
across the metropolitan area.
Citizens are being
ordered to stay inside.
You won't believe it!
[pants]
Take a look at this!
I rolled a super ultra-rare!
--[SARUTA] For real?!
--[KIJIBAYASHI] Wow!
Inukawa, did you spend
more money on...
[GROUP]
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
[whistle blows]
No one's allowed past
this point, even on foot.
Haven't you seen the news?
What should we do, Captain?
Guess we'll change course.
It's boring to see
the same scenery
all the time anyway.
[GODA]
Body Improvement!
[GROUP]
Fight on! Fight...
[SCAR 10A]
I knew there was somethin' off.
I guess the cars in the
sky were just a decoy.
Then there's likely
another group
sneaking around somewhere.
Right. Let's get some
information out of 'em.
[TERUKI]
So many Scars, but...
We have to do this.
Wait, your name's
Terada, isn't it?
I can't believe you'd
betray us like this!
And you're Ishihara from
Claw's 4th Division.
I can't believe your
rude accusation!
I was just acting as a spy
and gathering up some intel.
I have valuable
information on the enemy.
I'll give it to you if you let
me join HQ's operation.
Terada!
Wait, how could you?
[TERUKI]
This is a nightmare!
[MINEGISHI] Did you honestly
think you had a chance
because there were three of you?
The difference between
the Ultimate 5
and the rest of you
is like night and day.
[KUROSAKI]
We're almost there.
If we keep going
straight, we should--
[gasps]
Nobody move!
Something doesn't feel
right up ahead...
There's something there.
Yeah, what is it?
It's coming!
[SHIMAZAKI]
Greetings, Scars. Are you lost?
At first, I thought
you were a bunch
of sewer rats, scurrying
around in the dark and filth.
How unsightly.
I'll put an end
to this foolishness.
[DIMPLE]
There's a crowd.
I guess my best bet is to try
to blend in and lose him.
[TSUBOMI]
Whoa, that's amazing!
Who is he?
[GUY 10B]
Hey! Stop pushing, you jerk!
[MIKI]
He's kinda scary.
[DIMPLE]
No way! Of all people...
Tsubomi's here!
[DIMPLE] If anything
were to happen to her,
Shigeo would erase me!
I have to stop him!
[DIMPLE]
Full-power barrier!
[DIMPLE groans]
Huh?
[DIMPLE] He hit so hard,
he undid my possession!
A home run outta the park!
Wake up, Shigeo! Wake up!
[SHIBATA growls]
Why did Kageyama come
falling from the sky?
Maybe someone was tryin'
a long throw or somethin'.
[SHIMURA]
Hey, who's this dude?
[YAMAMURA] Those muscles
are pretty impressive.
Were you the one
who threw our friend
through the air like a football?
Kageyama is a member
of our club.
I don't know who you are,
but unless you want
trouble, I suggest--
[SHIBATA growls]
[GODA groans]
[ALL]
Captain!
Bastard! You can't
do that to him!
I'll show you how much
stronger I've gotten!
Demon Rush!
[SHIMURA]
It's our turn!
[ALL yell]
[ALL]
Fight!
[groans]
Onigawara!
[SHIBATA growls]
No way!
With one arm?!
[GROUP yells]
[SHIBATA yells]
[GODA grunts]
I don't know what you
have against Kageyama...
...but he doesn't
deserve to have you
step on his head!
He's a kind and decent guy.
Listen. You've been
working so hard.
No matter how many times
you've passed out...
you've stumbled...
You've always been
running right behind us.
You never give up.
Seeing you like that gives
the rest of us courage!
And that's not gonna break,
no matter what this guy does!
You hear me?!
I won't let you!
I'll die before I let you
do anything to Kageyama!
[yells]
[DIMPLE]
This is more like it!
He's totally ripped!
Here we go! Unleashed!
[yells]
[DIMPLE]
Don't look so surprised.
Muscles built using
psychic powers
don't stand a chance
against muscles built
by training hard
every single day!
This guy is way
outta your league!
Shigeo was right.
[SHIBATA groans]
[yells]
Hmph!
[GODA]
Hm?
[GROUP]
Captain!
[KUMAGAWA]
That was incredible!
Man, that was one hell
of an adrenaline rush!
You went at him like a beast!
All that training
paid off big time!
Wait, you mean I did that?
I think it's time for us
to celebrate your growth!
[GROUP] Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Crap! That freak's
gettin' up again!
No way!
What now, Captain?
What do we do?!
I don't know why, but
I can't raise my arms.
So much for trying
that a second time.
[ONIGAWARA]
Here he comes!
[GODA]
Kageyama!
[MOB]
The Body Improvement Club?
Oh. What happened?
Guess I was sleeping.
That was weird.
Be careful sleeping
outside. Not a good idea.
[MOB]
Sorry about that.
[MOB] What happened, Dimple?
Tell me everything.
[SHO]
Looks like we finally made it.
I'm coming for you,
Dad. Get ready.
[REIGEN]
After waking up, Mob heads
for Seasoning Cultural Tower.
There, he goes up against
Minegishi from the Ultimate 5!
Leave the strongest of those
guys, Shimazaki, to me!
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode 11:
"Guidance ~Psychic Sensor~."
Option B involves buying
the Blu-rays and the manga.