[MOB] Now I'll be able to
hit you with everything...
All my power...
...and all my rage.
[gasps]
[BOSS]
Is that it?
Looks like this is finally
getting interesting!
[laughs]
Look at you!
You're enjoying this,
too, aren't you?
[MOB laughs]
[KOYAMA]
What the hell is going on?
They're on a totally
different level.
[BOSS laughs]
[BOSS] As good and righteous
as you try to sound,
deep down, you're
the same as me.
[MOB grunts]
Shige!
[BOSS] How does it feel to be
released from your shackles?
We are freer than
anyone else in the world!
[gasps]
[RITSU]
Brother...
[gasps]
[MOB gasps]
[MOB whimpers]
[MOB] How...? How could
I be so foolish?
What's wrong with me?!
It may have only
been for a moment...
...but I let this
power control me!
You're so emotionally unstable.
At this rate, you'll
never catch up to me,
no matter how far
you go to do so.
I am the best in the world!
[MOB]
I don't get it.
How did your life end up
being so empty and hollow?
Though I suppose I
can't really judge you
for the life you chose.
You were just unlucky,
that's all.
Ha.
You're joking, right?
There's no one in
this whole world
who's as lucky... as me!
Heaven bestowed these
powers upon me
and made all of you
extras in my story,
solely here to make
my star shine!
[MOB]
Is that so?
Then it wasn't luck
that you were missing.
It was bonds.
What did you say?
I mean that, in your world,
you were the only
one who existed.
You lived in total solitude.
I know how that feels.
A life of loneliness,
one I want to forget...
I don't understand.
What is this?
Why are you crying?
[MOB] You might not believe
me when I say this,
but it's true.
I really don't wanna hurt you.
[BOSS]
Tsk!
I'm sorry...
[BOSS gasps]
[REIGEN]
What in the hell is going on?
[DIMPLE]
I have no idea.
The president's aura
has suddenly vanished.
Does that mean
it's finally over?
Yes! Way to go, Mob!
[TAKEUCHI]
Impressive.
Hard to believe that
boy's actually human.
That's true.
He's just a normal
middle school kid.
[RITSU]
You used a tremendous amount
of power once again.
Didn't you, brother?
[SHO]
It's not over yet.
[gasps]
My dad's aura didn't disappear.
It only changed.
[SHO]
He mentioned to me before...
When he's under a lot of stress,
that's when he's truly awakened.
[MOB grunts]
[grunts]
[BOSS yells]
This is completely
incomprehensible.
How can one man's powers
be so incredibly immense?
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo...
This is the one
time you shouldn't
try to do the impossible.
[TERUKI] He's already
using way more energy
than he did when beat me.
[REIGEN]
If you can't win,
then run.
You're not responsible
for any of this.
Mob.
[sighs]
I've never felt
like this before.
Now wake up.
If you think you're going
to give up after that,
you're sadly mistaken.
Open your eyes!
No, I'm done.
[gasps]
I hate to admit it...
...but I'm just
not strong enough.
I don't have what
it takes to show you
a new path to follow
in life. Sorry.
[BOSS]
Huh?!
You're the one who awakened
these destructive impulses!
Now you're going to have
to deal with them!
It's too late to
crawl off and hide
in your shell now!
[BOSS gasps]
[MOB]
I give up.
[MOB] I hoped you could
turn over a new leaf
and become a better person...
...but that hope is gone.
[BOSS yells]
It appears that...
[BOSS sputters]
...we're both influencing...
[yelps]
...each other quite a bit.
Yes.
But I failed at being
a good influence on you.
So that's it. At this
point, we both lose.
[groans, screams]
[MOB]
This is...
I think I'm about to die.
Mob, no!
[MOB gasps]
What's up, Shigeo?
--Hey, bro!
--[TERUKI] 'Sup?
Well done, kid.
[MOB]
No, this is nothing...
It doesn't come close to the
fear of losing all I have.
[MOB]
Body improvement!
Fight on!
[BOSS growls]
[MOB grunts, yells]
[MOB groans]
[MOB]
You're finished!
[growls]
[MOB] If something like
that makes it outside...
[MOB]
...it might...
I-I think it's gonna...
I think it's gonna explode!
[MOB]
Everyone! Run! Run away!
It's Mob! Look!
Whoa! He's alive!
[MOB] He ended up releasing
too much energy
and self-destructed!
You're bleeding like crazy!
[MOB]
Master! You need to run!
[gasps]
[MOB] All that's left is
a massive amount of energy.
It's just gonna keep
growing and churning...
...until it explodes
like a bomb!
And it looks like there won't
be any way to contain it.
So, let's hurry!
All right
I think we need
to get outta here.
We're gonna get caught up
in that if we stay.
[SERIZAWA] That's the
president's final light
flickering back there.
Our president who was trying
to take over the world.
[HATORI] Just shut up
and run! You're gonna die!
[DIMPLE] Hey, wait a second!
Where's Shigeo?!
Huh?!
[BOSS]
You made the right decision.
There's no avoiding this.
You have to sever
the energy source
before the explosion happens...
...by putting an end to my life.
[gasps]
Wait, what are you doing?
Containing the explosion.
So in the end, not
only were you unable
to defeat me, but you
also couldn't save
your friends or even yourself.
Such a tragedy.
Someone with your
abilities should've
been able to handle this better.
I may have powers, but they
don't fix everything.
And honestly,
that's fine with me.
Huh?
I still have a choice.
And I control my own destiny.
I get to be the protagonist.
It's my life.
[gasps]
[MOB]
That's why I chose to be here.
No matter how much
I dislike you,
I can't just leave you here
to suffer on your own.
That would be too sad.
And that's why I'm staying.
[BOSS]
What are you planning to do
with that filthy cat?
Aw, come on now.
After all, the poor
little thing was drenched
and shivering out in the rain.
And besides...
It'll help Sho learn
to be a gentle boy.
I mean, he is going
to grow up watching you.
We need to be gentle. Gentle.
I don't understand!
Why did you have
to be so violent?!
[BOSS]
Simple: it's pragmatic.
To lead an organization,
I need to establish
my dominance.
You can't control people's
hearts with psychic powers!
You're wrong. True
power is absolute.
And, as long as I have it,
people will believe in me.
Maybe some, but not everyone.
[BOSS]
Everyone.
Even our gentle little Sho
is starting to take an
interest in what I can do.
[WIFE]
Goodbye.
[BOSS]
What happened? When did I...?
--[MOB screams]
--[BOSS gasps]
[grunting]
[MOB]
If I can just absorb it...
[BOSS] Don't do it!
You'll only end up--
[yells]
[gasps]
[MOB] You wanted to
apologize, didn't you?!
Then you need to say it
loud and clear!
[screams]
You have to...
The same goes for me!
I need to tell someone how
I feel about them, too!
[REIGEN]
Mob...
[TERUKI muffled]
Kageyama!
[RITSU]
Shige!
[DIMPLE]
Hey! Wake up!
[TERUKI]
Can you hear us?
Say something!
Shigeo!
Brother, please!
He's coming around!
Let's dig him out.
[TERUKI]
Thank goodness you're okay.
[REIGEN]
Unbelievable.
Anyway, the sooner we can
get outta here, the better.
Can ya walk?
I think so...
[RITSU] Every one of our
wounds have been healed.
Our clothes are
in shambles, though.
Huh. Yeah, you're right.
What's up with that?
There, on the left
side of your chest.
[MOB]
Huh?
[DIMPLE] Pretty bold
fashion statement, kid...
I gotta say, Kageyama,
you never cease to
amaze me, ya know that?
Couldn't have picked
a better rival
to go up against.
Don't go wandering
off too far, okay?
[MOB] This ground...
It's not concrete.
My head is still spinning.
The sky seems cramped.
Where are we?
[REIGEN]
There's the exit.
Watch out for fallin' objects.
[TERUKI]
It's quiet.
I'm surprised there aren't any
news 'copters flying around.
Well, can you blame them?
I wouldn't come
anywhere near here
without knowing
if it's safe yet.
[MOB] Everything does seem
kinda quiet, though.
What's going on?
[REIGEN] I seriously
thought you were a goner
back there, Mob. Pretty scary.
I was sure ground
zero would've been
totally eviscerated.
Uh--
What the hell is that?
But what appeared
there happened to be...
Uh--
Hey!
[RITSU]
Whoa, Shige! Take it easy!
Can you walk?
'Cause your body's
been through a lot.
Don't worry, I'm okay.
No broken bones or anything.
But lately, whenever
I use a lot of power,
I have a hard time
staying awake afterward.
[RITSU]
Huh?
In that case, let me
carry you a bit.
You get some rest.
[RITSU] But, where do you
plan on carrying him?
Our house is...
Sorry.
He'll be able to fix up
your house good as new,
but he'll need three
days to do it.
Just three days?!
[REIGEN] Why don't you guys
crash at my place?
It'll be cramped,
but I'm sure we
can make it work.
Jeez! What's with the face?
I'm just tryin' to help!
Yeah, don't worry
about me. I'm good.
[RITSU] Would you mind if we
stopped by the school first?
[REIGEN]
At this hour?
[RITSU] There should be a spare
tracksuit in the club room.
[REIGEN]
Oh.
Good call.
[RITSU] I wonder if they'd
mind if I borrowed
one for myself, too.
I really shouldn't
without asking.
Tracksuit thieves! Stop!
[MOB]
Oh...
Hey, Captain.
[REIGEN]
I think I just peed a little.
[GODA]
You startled me.
I stopped by to grab
some dumbbells.
Wasn't expecting to see
anyone at this hour.
Sorry 'bout that.
You gave us a scare, too.
It's all good, I get it.
Hang on just a sec, okay?
Hey, how's it going?
Question for ya.
So, uh what's everyone from
the Body Improvement
Club doing here?
We were just stopping by to--
Bein' here this late
gave me an idea!
The Body Improvement
Club will now start
a three-day, four-night
strengthening hell
training camp!
Hang on. We're here to--
We should always
help each other out
when we're in need!
True, but we're really
tired and we just--
[GODA]
I'm sure you wanna sleep
on a giant futon, don'tcha?!
No! A small one's just fine!
[GODA] There's enough
room for all of you
over at my granny's house!
You'll need to gather
and make your own food,
so it'll be excellent training!
And it's just a
90-minute jog away!
Let's move out!
Wait! Reigen told us
earlier that we--!
That sounds great!
You guys take care, okay?
I'm gonna take a cab home.
--[RITSU screams]
--[GODA] Body Improvement!
[CLUB MEMBERS]
Fight on! Fight on!
[DIMPLE]
Man. Rough one.
I totally forgot!
I should've gone over to
Reigen's place after all.
[SARUTA] Uh... Is that
what I think it is?
[KIJIBAYASHI]
They say seeing is believing,
but honestly, I still
don't believe it.
No kidding.
I mean, how do you even go about
growing something like that?
[TOME] Come on, you guys!
Isn't it obvious?!
Aliens! This is the
work of aliens!
Awesome!
--[GUY 13B] It's beautiful.
--This simply must be...
...the work of our
beloved leader!
Crazy. A giant vegetable.
That thing's got "Mob"
written all over it.
No doubt!
[MITSUURA]
That's incredible!
So you're the ones
behind that giant plant?
Uh, well...
If you're asking if we were
directly involved, I guess
I'd have to say no.
I mean, we basically
were, though.
Huh?
Amazing! Fantastic!
[KUROSAKI]
Mitsuura...?
I'm sorry, but I think I'm going
to have to stop coming here.
What do you mean?!
Why would you stop?!
If everything goes well
with your research and
you actually develop
the technology to make espers
out of ordinary people...
...there might end up being
even more of these
misguided people
who misuse their powers.
I can't support
what you're doing
and I think you should stop.
I don't even need the money.
[ASAHI yelps]
She's right, this should stop.
Honestly, we're really
not that remarkable.
[HOSHINO yelps]
Are you sure, kids?
[MITSUURA whimpers]
Okay!
You're right.
I'll stop using you
for research.
[KAITO, DAICHI laugh]
[MITSUURA] But to be honest,
my favorite part of all this...
...is just spending
time with you guys.
You all wouldn't mind coming by
every once in a while
as friends, would ya?
What now?
What do you plan on
doing with your life?
The organization's gone.
So, I guess finding
another job is up first.
[KOYAMA]
Yeah. Same.
Now that there aren't any
more scars on my face,
maybe I'll start
up a ramen shop.
[SAKURAI] Scars or not,
I don't think the hospitality
industry is for you.
[KOYAMA]
You got anything lined up yet?
[SAKURAI] I've got an interview
at a convenience store.
What? You're really
gonna ask him?
Yes, I'm hoping
Master Reigen will
allow me to study under him.
Are you sure?
You're not exactly a
people person, you know.
[MUKAI] She's right. I mean,
you are kind of boring.
[MURAKI]
Uh...
[JOSEPH] So, it looks
like the government...
...determined that
this was the work
of a delusional criminal
organization, huh?
I can't believe you were
defeated by a civilian esper.
[BOSS]
It's the truth.
[JOSEPH]
Oof.
How embarrassing.
You give us pros a bad name.
What'll happen to my dad?
[JOSEPH]
Well, let's see...
Under normal circumstances,
he'd be executed.
But, who knows?
They might decide to keep him
alive as a research subject.
[SERIZAWA]
Why'd he have to say something
so harsh to his son like that?
[JOSEPH] Either way,
it's not my call to make...
...so I can't say for sure.
[SERIZAWA]
P-President! Wait a second!
[BOSS]
Serizawa.
Listen.
I never actually considered
any of you as my comrades.
So don't worry about me.
People are going to
try to manipulate you
because of your lack
of self-confidence.
Make sure you don't let them.
And, Sho.
I was hoping you'd
have the opportunity
to see your mother again
and reconnect with her.
But it seems my pride
severed that possibility.
I'm truly sorry about that.
[SHO]
Don't be.
I see Mom every now and then.
Believe it or not,
she's always asking me
how you're doing.
It's too bad.
Really wish I
could've stopped you
before she found out
what you'd become.
When I called her this morning,
she said she'd come
see you sometime.
So I wouldn't start thinking
this is all over with
if I were you.
You'll still get
an earful from Mom,
and believe me, you need it.
[BOSS] "People need
other people"... huh?
What? So it was only
a short circuit?
Apparently, a mouse
bit into some wires.
And since that's what
started the fire,
the insurance kicked in,
and bam! New office.
Which is great, except
for how boring it looks.
Okay, Mob, do your thing.
Right.
Good work. Thanks.
[gasps]
That hole in my pocket...
I just remembered.
That's where I put
those broccoli seeds
from the farm job.
Broccoli seeds?
Oh, well, it doesn't really--
[grunts]
Broccoli, huh?
[gasps]
[MOB]
Master, you mean that's...!
[REIGEN]
How about we play the
"just forget you
ever saw this" game?
Anyway, this guy sure is late...
Huh?
[REIGEN]
Oh, there you are.
Come in.
I got lost along the way.
I'm really sorry.
Thanks for the
other day, Kageyama.
What's with the suit?
Wait, are you gonna work here?!
[SERIZAWA]
Mm-hm.
Reigen was generous enough
to make me an offer.
He said it was something
that even I could handle.
And I figured it was the least
I could do after Claw...
caused so much trouble.
Our goal is to try
and make a better
tomorrow for everyone.
Are you with us?!
Uh, yes, sir! I'll do my best!
The client's gonna be here soon.
But before they get here...
Huh?
Time to re-do your do.
Whoa! That's amazing.
--[REIGEN] Hmm.
--He seems so different.
[REIGEN] I guess he at least
looks like he can pull off
customer service now.
Hold on. Did you say
customer service?!
What should I do when
a customer comes around?!
What was your last job?
[SERIZAWA] Uh, if people
showed up, my orders were
to start attacking them
with my umbrella.
What the hell, dude?
Ah, well, we can
make it work. Oh!
If you have any questions,
you can ask my
senior staff member.
Your what?
[REIGEN]
So, Mob.
Think you could
show him the ropes?
At least until he's
out of training.
Huh?
A pleasure to work with
you, Mr. Kageyama!
Huh? Oh, yeah.
A pleasure to work
with you, too...
[MOB]
What should I do?
Now I'm getting nervous.
[GUY 13C]
Uh, pardon me. Is this...?
[REIGEN]
Oh, hello there!
Really sorry about the mess.
Please have a seat.
Serizawa, get our
guest some tea.
[SERIZAWA]
T-Tea?
I-I'm sorry, I've never
made that before.
[DIMPLE]
We are so screwed.