[SERIZAWA]
Leave this place.
I don't want you to get hurt.
And take this guy
with you when you go.
He's supposed to be a hostage,
but I feel bad for him.
[MOB]
Oh, it's the prime minister.
[SERIZAWA]
What? Is that who you are?
So, I'm free to go, then?
Yes, sir.
Holy cow.
I just talked to
the prime minister!
You're part of the group
that abducted him.
How could you not know?
[SERIZAWA]
Well... I don't really watch TV.
So I guess that means...
...most people think we're
the bad guys, don't they?
[MOB] But you are.
Look at how much damage
you've done to the city.
[SERIZAWA]
It's fine.
The president said most people
had already
evacuated beforehand.
The president?
Yeah, that's right.
He's the one who hired me on.
In fact, considering the
hell that was my life,
you could say he rescued me.
What a pig sty.
You've lived like
this for 15 years?
Maybe. Who're you?
My name is Suzuki
and I'm here to help.
Your mother's concerned,
so she asked me to talk to you.
[SERIZAWA]
Great. Another counselor.
Look, man. Don't try
to get any closer,
or you'll get hurt.
I'm not exactly normal.
Yes, I know. I hear
that you're an esper.
I understand you better
than you may think.
[SERIZAWA]
Yeah, I'll bet. Go away.
[BOSS]
And why would I do that?
Why don't you tell me
how you're feeling?
[SERIZAWA]
N-No... Don't say anything else.
Please, I'm begging you.
Don't annoy me.
[BOSS]
It must be hard not being able
to make friends
because people think
your powers are creepy.
[SERIZAWA]
Stop it!
Don't act like you
know what it's like!
Just... Just go away!
[BOSS] People bullied you
out of your place
in society, didn't they?
[screams]
[SERIZAWA]
Get out!
[gasps]
[BOSS]
You see, I'm an esper, too.
I want you to come with me.
But I can't leave this room.
Whenever I do, I get dizzy.
[BOSS]
It was raining outside earlier.
But now, I'd like to give
this umbrella to you.
Just imagine that
when you're under it,
it's the same as
being in your room.
There's no reason to worry.
You'll be fine
if you're with me.
I'll show you how to harness
and control your powers.
[SERIZAWA] After that,
I became an upper echelon
employee of Claw and regained
my place in society.
Don't you think
that's kinda weird?
[SERIZAWA]
Huh?
I'm no expert, but it
just seems wrong to me.
Think about it.
Aren't you basically
being used here?
Say what?
[DIMPLE]
Look who's talkin'!
How rude! What a completely
horrible thing to say!
[MOB]
You're the one who's horrible.
If this was all you
were going to do,
you should've just
stayed a shut-in.
Don't you care how many
lives you've ruined?
[SERIZAWA]
The president told me that
world domination always
involves certain sacrifices.
[MOB]
Do you believe that, too?
Okay, that's enough.
I'm going to have to
ask you to leave again.
No, Serizawa. I won't.
You chose the wrong
person to follow.
Are you all right?
That umbrella...
Yeah, I noticed.
It's shrouded in some
pretty insane power.
[SERIZAWA] When I'm
under this, I feel safe.
It's just like being in my room.
If we can take that
thing away from him...
...then he'll lose
all his strength.
[SERIZAWA grunts]
Trying to immobilize me
isn't gonna work!
[gasps] That hurt.
Oh, uh, sorry. Are you okay?
You were faking?
[MOB]
Now, Dimple!
You got it!
[SERIZAWA screams]
Oh, crap!
He goes that nuts after only
a few seconds
without his umbrella?
He must have incredible anxiety.
He finally found someone
who understood him
and had no choice but to follow.
He never stood a chance
against someone
who used that
to their advantage.
I have to tell him.
I'm sorry to say this,
but your president
didn't give you peace.
He implanted the idea
that you can't survive
on your own to chain you
to the organization.
[laughs] So are you some
kind of counselor?
You can't rejoin
the world this way.
At this rate, if anything,
you won't ever be
able to come back.
Like a kid who still
has his whole life
ahead of him knows how I feel.
Then tell me...
What in the hell am I
supposed to do then?!
No one ever understood this
power I was born with!
People thought I was creepy,
so I'd lose control
and destroy things!
Then they'd scold me
and I'd lose control again!
I've even accidentally sent
my mother flying before!
I never knew when
I might totally snap!
There was never anybody
around who I could talk to.
'Cause I just wanted to...
I dunno... I just wanted...
I ju...
I just wanted to have friends.
I've made some friends
in this company.
And they're espers,
just like me!
You'd never understand!
[MOB]
Of course I do.
But, those people
aren't what you think.
Huh?
[MOB]
Because I actually have friends.
That's how I know.
They aren't your friends.
They're liars.
[stammers]
Shut up! I'm warning you!
This isn't good, Shigeo!
That's a lot of friggin' energy!
I won't let you go any further!
Those are the
president's orders!
He trusts me and I don't
wanna let him down!
Don't kid yourself!
This has nothing
to do with trust!
He doesn't really care!
He's just using you!
No! The president got
me out of that room
and gave me a reason to live!
Maybe, but he doesn't
see you as a person!
Why would you say that?
[MOB]
You said that you didn't wanna
hurt anybody, didn't you?
Then you're just like I am.
It might be hard
for you to admit,
but you have to know
you're wrong.
Shut up!
Listen...
I'll be your friend--
you have my word!
[yells]
--[DIMPLE] Huh?
--[SERIZAWA] Uh...
Whoops. I shot at him.
Shigeo!
But I went all out!
What?!
It feels like you're
sucking up part of my energy.
I can sense everything
you're feeling.
So much of your energy is sad.
You took it and turned it
into your own power?
Yeah, I did. But, here.
You can have it back.
[SERIZAWA]
What am I seeing?
Wait...
He's...
He's the same as me...
[BOSS]
Due to this little uprising
you and your friends led,
I'm going to have to
recruit more soldiers.
Please, Dad, you've
gotta stop this.
None of those guys
are of much help to you.
You know that.
Since you're my son,
I'm going to let you
in on a little secret.
The project of applying stress
to normal human beings
to awaken any ESP they may have?
It was a failure.
Even if it did happen to
stir up some latent skills,
the results were
insignificant at best.
[SHO]
But, wait. I saw them.
Are you calling those
powers insignificant?
You mean the ones
they're out there using
like there's no tomorrow?
Those happen to be my powers.
I'm able to share my abilities
with anyone I choose.
At the same time, I can absorb
other people's
abilities as my own.
That's what gives
me the upper hand,
and I've kept this
secret from everyone.
You're saying you gave
those 600 soldiers
out there your power?
[BOSS]
And that's just a mere fraction
of the energy I've
accumulated over the years.
But just because it's a fraction
doesn't make it any less vital.
I'll be reclaiming my energy
from those who have lost.
I finally get it.
My dad's not human.
He's a monster
made up of energy!
There's a lesson that can
be learned here, Sho.
And that would be that
only one absolute being
can be the true
protagonist of this world.
[SHO]
Absolute being?
[gasps]
[SHO]
Wait! You're--!
You're Ritsu's older brother.
If you're here,
then that must mean
my detonator went off
the way I hoped it would.
Does that mean you're the one
who set my house on fire?
Hmph. You're probably
pissed about that.
Either way, I'd suggest
you leave here.
There isn't anyone in the world
who can defeat my dad.
I'm not mad anymore.
I'm sure there's a lot
you're trying to deal with.
I mean, look at what
your own father
has done to you.
And who are you?
[MOB] He's been worried
about you losing control
for a long time now. I can tell.
Because my younger brother
was afraid of me, too.
[SHO]
Whoa... He's changed.
[BOSS]
Don't pretend like you know
what's going on with our family.
Serizawa filled me in a little.
He said that your son was
up here trying to stop you.
He said you'd
beaten him so badly,
he couldn't bear to watch
and came downstairs...
He felt so pathetic
for not stepping in,
he wanted to disappear.
So then Serizawa
lost, I take it?
That moron must've
gotten sloppy.
No, you're wrong.
Human relationships
aren't so easily defined
as just "winners" and "losers."
It was the president who finally
got me to leave that room.
I'm grateful to him.
Even so, I don't
understand the need
for us to hurt people.
I've been too scared
to think about it,
so I just didn't.
But if my happiness can only
come from someone else's tears,
then it's not something
I want in the first place.
Thank you for making
me realize that.
Apparently, trash will never be
anything more than trash.
So be it.
I've never really counted
on other people anyway.
Bonding with them is an empty
and meaningless gesture.
And at the end of the day,
I am wholly complete
while on my own.
But that's not true at all.
You just don't get it.
Everyone grows because
of the encounters
they have with others.
People need other
people in their lives.
And, someday, you'll
need them, too.
When that day comes,
you're going to regret it.
Let me help you.
When you need somebody
to talk to, I'll be there.
You want to be a shoulder
I can lean on?
[BOSS chuckles]
Save that kind of talk
for the pathetic
weaklings of the world.
There's something
you should know.
My dad has the ability
to give people
his energy while
stealing theirs.
On top of that,
he's got a massive
30-year stockpile of
energy at his disposal.
Meanwhile, I can
barely even move...
If that's the case,
maybe I can help you.
[SHO]
Hm?
[gasps] Amazing...
[BOSS gasps]
[BOSS]
He has the same power as me?
Can you move?
[SHO] Y-Yeah, I can
sorta stand, at least.
Good to hear.
I suggest you evacuate.
I'm going to do my best to--
[BOSS]
You are my rival.
[grunts]
[SHO]
Dad! No!
[SHO yells]
Stay out of this.
He has the potential to
become my mortal enemy.
Listen. I only came
here to talk to you.
Just give it up, Shigeo!
You can't talk to guys like him!
You're annoying.
Begone.
Dimple, no!
[TERUKI]
Was it really a good idea
to let him go in alone?
I've never seen
my brother openly
call out his authority
like that before.
He looked like he was
in pain to me, though.
He's not usually the type
to charge into a fight.
What do you think, Reigen?
Any insight?
At first glance,
Mob may look unreliable,
but you can't deny his strength.
You're talking about his
insane telekinesis, right?
[REIGEN]
That's part of it.
But it's just one of the
qualities I'm referring to.
What makes him truly great
is his ability to tell people
exactly how he feels.
And that speaks to
their heart far more
than anything else could.
By expressing those feelings,
Mob's honest nature
helps others--
Uh--
It's Dimple!
What's wrong? Are you
okay? Where's Mob?
I don't know, but things are
lookin' pretty bad here.
That Boss guy seemed
hell-bent on killing Shigeo.
[REIGEN]
Four-eyes. You got a sec?
Huh?
Now, what was it you
wanted to tell me?
[MOB] You said that
bonding with others
is empty and meaningless.
But, you couldn't be more wrong.
No one's born complete.
Everybody's lacking something.
Helping each other is what
gives our lives meaning.
All of you are so
myopic and boring.
Even among those who happen
to be blessed with
the gift of ESP,
my powers surpass each one.
When I came to
that realization,
it appeared as though
the entire world
could fit right in
the palm of my hand.
That was when I was
in middle school,
the same age you two are now.
While I followed my destiny,
you both let your minds put
a halt to all progress,
leaving you to live
the same boring,
mundane existence as the
powerless ones around you.
No.
You're the one who's been stuck
in the same mindset
since middle school.
There are far more unique people
in this world than
you seem to believe.
And just as many
views and outlooks.
No one should be able
to place a value
on another person's way of life.
Don't give me that "moral
high ground" routine.
I have no need to rely
on others to make up
for any deficiencies I have
because I have the
ability to steal, use,
and rule as I see fit.
My goal in life is to leave
a huge mark upon this world.
And now is the time for
that goal come to fruition.
[grunts]
[SHO]
Hey. Listen.
Don't worry about me.
Just finish him!
How foolish.
And to think I had
actually considered
letting you inherit the world
I was going to take over.
But apparently, Sho,
you have become a failure.
Hey...
[BOSS]
Are you angry on Sho's behalf?
[BOSS laughs]
[BOSS]
You truly are a simple child.
You need to shut your mouth.
Still, I'm game. Show me
everything you've got.
[gasps]
[MOB]
Oh, man... This is rough...
Stop it!
[groans]
[BOSS]
Watch carefully.
This is what happens
to those who are weak.
[groans]
[BOSS] You have some nerve
trying to lecture me
when you're so feeble.
You've wasted my time.
[REIGEN]
Don't move.
[BOSS]
Hmm?
This thing's loaded, by the way.
[BOSS]
Sakurai's Jugan.
You're going to need much more
than that to threaten me.
M-Master...
Mob, stay still.
I'm not sensing any kind
of power from you at all.
You'll stay out of this if you
know what's good for you.
Huh?
Apparently, you still
don't understand
how powerful I am.
[REIGEN]
Hey.
You still alive, Mob?
[REIGEN] I don't know
what I was thinking,
letting you go off
alone like that.
My mind was probably distracted
by all the weirdness
goin' on around me...
I failed as a master.
You did well.
I'll buy you some takoyaki
on our way home.
He calls you "Master"?
Even though you lack the skills
to see how powerful I am?
So you're also
somebody who tricks
others and steals from them.
Interesting.
[REIGEN]
Well, this is ironic.
Look, if you ask me,
you're pretty short-sighted.
'Cause you only see
unseen powers.
Gotta say, I feel sorry for ya.
[BOSS]
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm saying, ESP
is great and all,
but it's not the only cool
power people can have.
And that's going
to be your downfall.
Off the top of my head, I can
think of four ways to beat you.
[BOSS]
Really?
You should give
them a try, then.
Oh, no, I didn't mean me.
However, I do have a request.
Will you let me join your side?
[BOSS]
And what good does that do me?
[REIGEN] I could easily
persuade my student,
who's unconscious
there to do so, too.
And all the guys on the ground.
That should be reason enough.
[BOSS]
Maybe if you tell me about these
methods of defeating me...
If you actually have any.
[REIGEN] Allow me to
fill you in on some powers
other than ESP that
you're not aware of.
As for the first one...
It's something that
espers should really
be extremely cautious about.
And that is...
...brute strength, ya moron!
[REIGEN gasps]
[BOSS] It makes sense you two
are master and student.
What a pair of fools.
[REIGEN]
Uh--
Wait! Time out! I give up!
I'll do anything
you want me to.
You have put me in
an extremely foul mood.
[REIGEN] N-N-No, wait!
Let's talk about this!
[REIGEN gasps]
No!
What's going on up there?
Please be okay.
Made it just in time.
President.
For once in my life,
I'm trying to be courageous.
Serizawa.
You've completely
betrayed me now.
And you know what that means.
[MOB]
Forget it.
[gasps]
[MOB]
That's enough talk.
Huh...?
[MOB] Let me just tell
you one last thing.
Those who don't understand
the feelings of others...
Ah, what's the point?
Some people have to
learn the hard way.
Is that...?
It's my brother.
Shigeo...
Mob just lost it.
Is... Is there anything I can
do to try and help you guys?
Hey, Serizawa.
Take my master and
the others and evacuate.
Your punishment comes first!
[yelps]
[SERIZAWA]
Shigeo!
Holy crap.
Look!
[REIGEN, SERIZAWA scream]
Where's Shige?
[gasps]
Are those plants?
Look at that.
So, the boss really did
cast Serizawa aside.
Sorry, who?
I apologize, but I
definitely owe him.
[HATORI]
Don't do it, Minegishi!
You don't wanna
piss off the boss!
Glad to see you're
alive, Hatori.
Minegishi, too...
Hmph!
It seems I'm now in a situation
where anybody can betray me.
It's back to the drawing
board, I suppose.
Disappear.
[ALL yell]
Disappear. Disappear. Disappear.
[BOSS cackles]
[yells]
Well, you're enthusiastic,
aren't you?
You're too weak to challenge me.
I'm still only using ten
percent of my energy.
If that's your 100 percent,
then this is pointless.
[BOSS gasps]
What the hell is that?
I see what's happening here.
You were provoking
an internal reaction.
Now I'll be able to hit
you with everything.
All my power...
...and all my rage!
[REIGEN] The final battle
begins between a furious
Mob and the arrogant
energy demon, Suzuki.
Careful! Don't push
yourself too hard, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II : episode 13.
"Boss Fight ~The Final Light~."
Watching the finale in real
time is an excellent decision.