[groans]
It's so slow lately
and I'm bored.
Well, that just
means there aren't
any spirits out there
bothering people, right?
[REIGEN]
It is peaceful...
[MOB]
It sure is.
But at this rate, we'll starve!
[REIGEN]
So we're gonna have to drum up
some work on our own.
[MOB]
Urban legends?
[REIGEN]
Yeah.
I'm sure you've talked
about stuff like that
with your friends at least
once or twice, right?
[MOB]
Not really.
Seriously?
'Cause when I was a kid,
those sorts of things
were all the rage.
Hanako of the Toilet,
the Human-Faced Dog.
Or the Dragger, if you want
somethin' a little newer.
My plan is to scour
the internet for local hits
about anything having
to do with urban legends.
That sounds even harder
than catching a tsuchinoko .
Nah, not really.
The Dragger's just a
story someone made up.
It's not like that
girl actually exists.
Then why look into it?
[REIGEN]
Places where urban legends
are popular tend to
have a lot of people
who believe in them
living in that area.
Which means tons of people there
will be looking
to buy an exorcism.
Why do you look happy
talking about sad people?
The secret to door-to-door
sales is a confident smile!
That desk's kinda short.
It was cheap.
What's with all the cold stares?
[MOB] Are we blocking
the street or something?
[BANSHOMARU]
Hey, you there!
Who gave you permission
to do business here?
Don't you know this area
belongs to me,
Banshomaru Shinra,
the greatest psychic
of the century?
[MOB] He's the greatest
of the century, too...?
What do you mean, "belongs"?
You're obviously not with
the Rising Sun Spiritual Union.
No, I'm a free agent.
Name's Reigen Arataka.
If you're another con ar--
I mean, uh, businessman,
do you think you could
hook me up with a few jobs?
The work's been
really slow lately.
Hmph! It would be
pretty stupid of me
to help out a business
rival, wouldn't it?
Now go on, and get outta here!
Not a chance.
What right do you have
to order me around?
[BANSHOMARU] You are breaking
so many city codes.
Oh, that's rich comin'
from somebody like you!
And what's that supposed
to mean exactly?!
[CUSTOMER 02A]
Excuse me...
Sorry to bother you,
but are you really a psychic?
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am!
[CUSTOMER 02A]
I'm so glad.
I was hoping you could help me.
[BOTH]
With pleasure! Sure!
[BANSHOMARU] So, what
seems to be the trouble?
Since childhood, it seems
I've always attracted spirits.
Ghosts and other
supernatural phenomena
are drawn to me like a magnet.
There's one here now.
Right next to me.
What? There's nothi--
Ah, yes. I can see it.
Hey, you shouldn't
lie to the client.
What did you just say to me?
Ugh, get a load of this guy.
There is nothing worse
than having to work
alongside frauds and liars.
Am I right, Mob?
I see the spirit of
a middle-aged man.
Oh, that side! Of course.
Thank goodness.
You are legit psychics.
Last time, I searched for help
on the internet. But all I
found were a bunch of phonies.
Hey, what is it
you're writing down?
I've never even thought
about making a website.
I gotta up my online game.
[CUSTOMER 02A] Lately,
there's been an especially
foul energy building
up around me.
I've managed to ward off
its effects with salt,
piling it on plates in my room.
Ah. Yes.
Spiritual texts do refer to
the efficacy of salt plates.
That's right.
That's why I ordered
extra salt on these fries.
To deter spirit intrusion.
Hey, Mob.
Don't eat too many of those.
[MOB]
Huh?
[CUSTOMER 02A]
I think there's been an increase
in my own sense of
dread lately due to
the urban legends
connected with this town
that keep spreading.
[CUSTOMER 02A]
The human-faced dog.
Dash Granny. The Red Raincoat.
And the Dragger.
I beg of you, please get rid
of the urban legends
plaguing us.
Uh, well, I'm sorry, but I
can't just go around and--
Leave it all to me,
Reigen Arataka!
I swear I'll take care of them!
[gasps]
So, which course would
you like to go with?
Which course?
We have a special right
now on weekend rates.
[BANSHOMARU]
You surprised me.
Can't believe you took the job.
And you want 20,000 yen
if you succeed?
It does get that
expensive, right?
Our base package
starts at 200,000 yen.
So I figure the final bill
for this would run
well over 500,000--
Well, I really appreciate
you helping me on this one.
[BANSHOMARU]
Huh? Wait, what did he just say?
[REIGEN] Come on,
let's get movin' on this.
Time's a wastin'!
Mister... Bashinmarsha?
Banshomaru Shinra!
And I'm not helping you, jerk!
You sat with her
and heard her out.
No running away.
[BANSHOMARU]
Oh, no, I refuse!
I'll cut you in on
the pay, of course.
I say we split up and
start questioning people.
Here's my info.
Be sure to stay in touch
with any updates.
[BANSHOMARU]
Hmph.
Whatever, fine.
I guess I'll chalk
this one up as charity.
Great! Thanks a bunch!
[REIGEN]
He wasn't busy, anyway.
Hey, Mob. Is Dimple around?
Dimple, he's calling you.
What now?!
I stay in extra-invisible
mode just to avoid you.
Ah, come on, don't be like that.
We're co-workers now, aren't we?
Like hell we are!
You just boss me around
like I'm some--!
Keep a close eye on the
fatso we're working with.
Use your stealth mode.
Well what's the point in that?
If he skips out on
the job, who cares?
[REIGEN]
Think he's the kinda idiot
who never deviates
from the manual.
But on this job, if anything bad
should happen to him,
as team leader, it'd be on me.
Come on, Dimple, please?
Help us avoid any accidents.
Okay, I'll do it. It's
give-and-take, though.
Someday, I'll need
a favor from you two,
and you'd better
deliver, ya got it?!
You sensing anything, Mob?
Yeah. Our client
was absolutely right.
There's something
wrong with this town.
There may really be something
sinister at work here.
[MOB] Why are we at
an internet café?
Because if we went around
questioning little kids,
somebody might call the cops.
[MOB] Wow, it's all people
insulting one another.
[REIGEN] Ugh. Finding
anything useful in all this
trolling would be like...
Oh! Look!
Somebody saw something!
A man in red?
Yeah, he was here a minute ago.
He tried to talk to us
but we both ran off.
What? You just saw him?
Where? Where was he?
I've gotta find him!
[GIRL 02B]
Ow! Let go of me, you weirdo!
This guy is scaring me!
[BANSHOMARU]
Ah! Sorry! I got excited.
But not like,
that kind of excited!
Wait, why are you
looking at me like that?
[GIRL 02C]
Yeah... We're outta here.
[BANSHOMARU]
Hold on!
It's not safe for
you two out there!
[GIRL 02B] Stay away from me!
This man's a pervert!
--[alarm beeps]
--[BANSHOMARU gasps]
Please, you misunderstood me!
I'm not trying to--
[BANSHOMARU gasping]
[BANSHOMARU] N-No! I'm not
a pervert! I'm a psychic!
An accredited member of
society! For real! See? Look...
Did he say a "psychic"?
Sounds pretty shady...
Ow! Hey, don't
throw rocks at me!
Ow!
Ugh, what a creepy guy.
Wait, I need to
get clues from you!
[RAINCOAT]
Girls! Come back!
[BANSHOMARU]
Was that him?
Get back here, damn you!
[BANSHOMARU] You're the
Red Raincoat, aren't you?
Don't get in my way!
[RAINCOAT]
It's no fun showing what's
"under the hood" to men!
[BANSHOMARU] A flasher who
goes after little girls, huh?
You criminal!
[BOY 02C]
Look! It's weirdo vs weirdo!
[BOY 02D]
Make sure you're recording this!
[BOY 02D chuckles]
[BANSHOMARU]
Ha, ha!
I was vice president
of the Sumo Club
in elementary school, you know!
[RAINCOAT]
I give up! I give up! Let me go!
You caught me...
Or so you think.
I was on the track team
in middle school, fatso!
[BOY 02C]
What a cheater.
[BOY 02D]
He is pretty fast, though.
[DOG panting]
[REIGEN] This is the
human-faced dog, huh?
That's magic marker. I guess
it was bad information.
Nope. This is the
real deal, all right.
I'm not sure I understand.
Most rumors end up being
stupid stuff like this.
To the kids, this little
guy is the real thing...
Hey, buddy.
Look! Somebody's at our
human-faced dog's doghouse.
Let's charge a viewing fee!
Could you tell us who the
owner of this dog is?
[BOY 02F] Yeah, it's the
old man who lives here.
[BOY 02E] He's got bad eyesight
so he can't see the scribbles.
Uh, are you three
guys his grandsons?
[BOY 02E]
Huh? Why would you think that?
Listen up, you dirt bags!
Draw another face on this dog
and I will beat the
living hell outta you!
He said all that
after he hit us.
I'll tell the PTA about this.
Go right ahead, I don't care.
What the world needs
is more grown-ups
who can put little brats
like you in your place.
That kind of crap might
work on your teachers,
but it won't work
on me, Taro Suzuki!
But you're still gonna
use a fake name, huh?
[OLD MAN 02A]
Wanna wash Terror for me, do ya?
That's very nice.
Tell me, is he really
filthy or something?
Ah, go ahead, either way.
[REIGEN]
Here you go, Terror.
[REIGEN] Who's a good boy?
You're a good boy!
Now. Let's get some
before and after pictures
to show the client what
we were able to find out.
You sure you don't
just like dogs?
Did you know the
human-faced dog
was a prank from the beginning?
Of course I did.
There's not really a dog with
an actual human face, get real.
Aw! Good doggie!
Let's ask your owner if we
can get some hot water, okay?
[panting]
[BANSHOMARU]
What's wrong? Out of breath?
Too bad for you!
I was in the Sumo Club
in elementary school,
but I was in the Ping Pong
Club in middle school!
I've got a ton of stamina,
so just bring it on!
[RAINCOAT]
You're totally out of breath.
Look, dude. Why're you
following me, anyway?
This isn't your problem.
Ever heard of a
citizen's arrest?
If I catch you in the act,
I can apprehend you
even without a badge!
Now, it's time to face justice!
It's over, perv!
Did you really think you'd
trapped me, fat boy?!
I was just luring you out here!
[screaming]
[RAINCOAT] I admit, this all
began as just a weird kink.
But eventually, I started to get
off on the whispers and rumors
I heard about myself in town.
It made me feel like a big man.
It made me feel as
powerful as a god!
Just by putting on this
raincoat and running around!
You're gonna turn me over
to the cops, is that it?!
Try it and see what
happens, you pig!
[BANSHOMARU screaming]
[RAINCOAT chuckles]
[RAINCOAT]
He passed out.
But people know what
I look like now.
And that'll make things
around here even tougher.
Might be time to go...
Huh?
[RAINCOAT]
Hmm?
Oh, I didn't see you there.
Were you watching me?
Hey. Tell me, are you thirsty?
[RAINCOAT]
Are you crazy or something?
Hey. Tell me, are you thirsty?
Uh-huh.
I'm parched!
Then I'll give you
plenty to drink!
[RAINCOAT screaming]
Spirit Hold!
Okay! That's as far as you go!
Damn! My body's still worn out!
[gasps]
[BANSHOMARU]
Where'd she go?
[yelling]
[choking]
Reigen's insurance
sure paid off.
[DIMPLE]
What power!
I can feel the spiritual
energy pouring off her!
I'll try pushing this guy's
latent abilities to the limit!
Here goes!
Hey. Tell me, are you thirsty?!
Are you flirting?
'Cause I'm not a fan of
women who are too pushy!
Take this!
[groans]
[yelping]
Whether or not I buy
into this manual,
it sure did come in handy!
[DIMPLE yells]
[DIMPLE]
Gotta keep him alive!
So we're getting out of here!
This is an SOS!
[REIGEN]
There we go! All clean!
Oh, man. Mob, if I
didn't know any better,
I'd say you just
jumped in a pool.
Guess I shouldn't have helped.
[phone ringing]
[REIGEN]
Hello, Reigen here.
Ah, got any info on--
Let's go.
Looks like he ran
into the Dragger.
She's one of the most popular
urban legends of modern times.
Maybe that's because of all the
talk about her on social media.
Either way, she's way
more powerful than most.
Looks like she can shapeshift
to suit her needs, too.
[gasps]
[yells]
[OHIKI screams]
He snapped his Achilles tendon!
This fatso needs to hit the gym!
Please, Dimple. Come on.
If this guy should
die under my watch,
Shigeo's not gonna
trust me anymore.
And I can't let that happen!
One day, that boy's
gonna be a big star.
So I'm gonna do whatever I
can to never let him down.
Oh, crap.
[OHIKI screams]
[MOB]
Thanks. Good work, Dimple.
[REIGEN]
Ooh! So that's the Dragger, huh?
Amazing!
Gotta take a quick
photo as proof.
Huh? She doesn't show
up on the screen.
[MOB gasps]
She's gone!
[DIMPLE] That monster you just
saw was created by rumors.
Which makes it hard
to categorize her
as "real" or "fake."
What do ya mean?
[DIMPLE]
She manifested in this world
by feeding off the imagination
and curiosity of
countless people.
Her appearance, her strength--
it was all decided by humanity!
[REIGEN] So mankind's image
of her became real?
[BANSHOMARU]
Yes, that's right.
We know who the Dragger is,
so we can't exorcise her.
What? And why not?
You were once a kid
who was terrified of things
that went bump in
the night, weren't you?
Yeah, I guess we all were.
The Dragger appears
in the evening,
when you're going
home from school.
She kidnaps kids and drags
them into the swamp.
I never believed in Santa Claus,
but if I found myself alone on
a street corner in the rain...
...I got goosebumps.
[BANSHOMARU]
The terror we felt back then
is still burned into our brains.
Even now, I'm shaking
just thinking about it.
[REIGEN] So this cold
sweat I have right now
is because I'm
instinctively afraid of her?
For a symbol of fear like that,
the power of someone
who's afraid
serves as nothing but food.
My spiritual power
didn't work on her.
She absorbs the energy of
those who are frightened,
getting stronger and stronger.
Attacks will just
make things worse.
Then I guess all
we can do is run.
We're done, Mob.
It's time to go.
Uh! Whoa! What the hell?!
[BANSHOMARU]
I-I can't get out!
[DIMPLE] It's the Dragger!
This is her doing.
[roars]
[REIGEN]
She's gigantic!
[REIGEN, BANSHOMARU yelling]
Careful, Mob!
She's probably gonna try
to absorb your power, too!
No, take a closer look at her.
He's doing it!
[gasps]
[DIMPLE]
Ah, that's right!
Shigeo is different!
He was never a part
of those groups
that shared urban legends,
creepy gossip, or ghost stories!
He was isolated from
those childhood fears!
So he doesn't even know
what's supposed to be scary
about the Dragger!
[OHIKI screams]
[MOB] She's a rainy-day
monster, right?
I mean, that's sorta
scary, isn't it?
You don't get it at all!
The Dragger's got the
grip of a giant bear!
Once she digs her claws into
you, you can never escape!
She can swim across
a lake in 20 seconds!
I see! That's her
character profile, huh?
You're thinking about
her like someone
on a tv show or a
D&D game, aren't you?
Come on, Mob!
You could at least pretend
to be scared or surprised.
This is why nobody
wants to talk to you.
Hold on. I thought you said
I didn't need to be
like other people.
[REIGEN]
Yeah, but when you grow up,
being able to socialize
becomes more important.
[BANSHOMARU] I guess I got
hurt when I passed out there,
didn't I?
But thanks. This was a
valuable experience for me.
Now I'm gonna head down
to the police station
to talk about that flasher.
Suppose this is goodbye.
[BANSHOMARU groans]
See ya. You take care, now.
One last thing
before we go home.
Let's go look into that
Dash Grannie, okay?
[REIGEN]
We're here at the perfect time.
Keep your eyes peeled
and stay focused.
[DASHING GRANNIE panting]
[ALL]
Huh?
[DASHING GRANNIE panting]
[REIGEN]
There she is! It's really her!
Go for it, Mob!
What the--?!
One more time...
Huh?
Hey, Shigeo, what's wrong?!
Yeah, hurry! Now!
[MOB] I can't exorcise
her. What do I do?
She's a lot more powerful
than the Dragger ever was.
We're doomed.
[BOTH]
You're kidding me!
[REIGEN] Oh crap, oh crap,
oh crap, crap, crap, crap!
What do we do?
The only thing we can do!
Run for it! Move!
[DIMPLE]
What happens if she catches us?
It's said that she grabs
her victims from behind
and strangles them to death!
Don't stop running! If she
catches you, you're dead!
You're falling behind, Mob!
--[REIGEN chuckles]
--[DIMPLE sighs]
[REIGEN] So. It was just an
old woman going for a run.
Hey, what happened?
I thought you could
use your physic powers
to move really fast, Shigeo!
What are you crying about?
I run all the time with the
Body Improvement Club...
...and I lost to an old woman.
Hey, come on! This
isn't a competition!
Well, I did get a
photo for our client.
I'd say we're done here.
[NARRATOR]
And with that, Dash Grannie
became the first urban legend
that traumatized poor Mob.
[REIGEN]
Boom! Did it!
Take a look, Mob!
This update will get
us more jobs, for sure!
[DIMPLE]
Hmm?
What is this crap?
Looks like GeoCities.
[REIGEN]
Wow! My fantastic new homepage
is getting us so many jobs now!
Bring it on!
But something's wrong with Mob!
Hey, what's the matter?
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode three:
"One Danger After Another:
Degeneration."
Recording it? Also an
excellent decision.