[REIGEN] Man, I climbed
the ladder enough
to be on television.
These greenrooms are nice,
but they definitely
make you feel antsy.
Okay, Reigen. You're up.
All right. It's showtime.
[BANSHOMARU]
Ah, here we go.
Master Jodo's return
to television.
[BANSHOMARU]
What?! Reigen?!
What's he doing there?
And now, we find
out if our guests
can save the poor,
unfortunate young man
who's been possessed!
Before that, I should introduce
our assembled connections
to the spirit world.
Though he needs no introduction,
president of the
Rising Sun Spiritual Union,
Master Kirin Jodo!
He's solved even
the most devastating
supernatural problems
and is the best of the best!
Our other guest is making
his first appearance
on television,
Mr. Reigen Arataka!
[clears throat] Hey.
Hello out there, everyone.
Reigen Arataka.
My business is
in Seasoning City.
So tell us, what would you say
are some of your most notable
accomplishments as a psychic?
[REIGEN]
Hm.
It's hard to pick
just one of them.
Well, I did defeat the
Dragger, so there's that.
What? That's awesome!
Then we should expect to see
some great things
from you today!
Now, let's bring out
the young man.
As we foresee things
of an unpredictable
nature taking place,
we have him securely
bound with restraints.
[babbling]
[AUDIENCE gasps]
[EBIHARA]
So, what do ya think?
Uh-huh...
I believe the footage
we just watched
moments ago mentioned
that he was possessed
by a fox after playing
the Kokkuri game.
Specifically, it's the
ghost of a Ruppell's fox,
usually found in North Africa.
[EBIHARA]
That's amazing!
You deduced precisely
what kind of ghost it is!
Have anything to add,
Master Jodo?
The poor child.
Strapped down like that...
I hope we don't have to keep
him bound much longer.
[EBIHARA]
I feel the same way.
I'm sure everyone watching
at home does, too.
And now, as promised,
we're going to witness
the public exorcism!
Right after an important
word from our sponsors.
When we're back,
we'll have Master Jodo
perform the exorcism.
Wait. Why don't we allow Reigen
to make the attempt, instead?
Wha--?!
[JODO] No one wants to see
an old man doing this.
Rather than show the world
the same-old-same-old,
why not let the country
see what a next-generation
psychic can do?
Whoa, wait a second!
I thought I was only
supposed to sit here
and comment today!
I was just trying to
give you an opportunity
to be in the spotlight.
But, if you're not
up to the task...
I'll do it, as scripted.
[REIGEN]
"Scripted"?
[REIGEN gasps]
I get it!
Hold up!
I'm happy to do it.
Sure, that's fine.
Reigen's gonna perform
the exorcism, guys!
--[JODO cackles]
--[AD] We're back in five!
[EBIHARA] We're back,
everyone, and now it's time
for the public exorcism!
The one performing
this feat is an exciting
newcomer who's had
a meteoric rise
in the psychic world!
Master Reigen Arataka!
Are you ready to do this?
Leave it all to me!
That's right!
Reigen Arataka is on it!
Mark my words,
this fox spirit's
as good as gone!
[REIGEN] Live or not, this
is still a television show.
Everything that
happens is a setup
written by some scriptwriter.
If I make this look
like the real deal,
that'll be the cue for
the boy to calm down
and the studio
audience to applaud.
The host will praise me,
and then the show will be over.
[yells]
[REIGEN]
Salt Splash!
Whoa!
He started throwin' a ton
of salt all over the place!
The spirit possessing
the boy seems
to be struggling in agony!
It's working!
It's really working!
[REIGEN]
But it's never worked before!
Not even once!
Just as I thought!
This kid's an actor!
Now that I know that for sure,
I'm not pullin' any
punches! Here we go!
[REIGEN]
Sorcery Crush Special!
Air Banishing Salt...
Punch!
It's a clean hit!
Well, I'd say it's been
about 30 minutes now
since Reigen started
the exorcism...
...but apparently, the spirit
just refuses to leave.
Talk about resilient.
[REIGEN]
Holy Water Chop!
Take a hint, kid!
I've already used
all my special moves.
Now I'm trying to keep things
going by makin' stuff up!
All right, why don't we have
our other psychic step in?
Huh?
[EBIHARA] Master Jodo,
if you wouldn't mind.
[REIGEN] Wait a second.
Was I just an opening act?
Is the old man gonna
take all the glory?!
Whoa, time out!
I've almost got it.
Switching right now might
be detrimental to the--
We're live. We gotta
move this along.
You've done some great work
over the last 30 minutes.
[REIGEN growls]
You schemin' old geezer!
All right then, Master Jodo!
Let's see you work!
[REIGEN]
My spotlight!
What am I supposed
to exorcise here?
This boy isn't even possessed.
He's just acting.
[REIGEN]
Huh?!
[REIGEN] Oh, come on!
Get a clue already!
Why'd you ruin all that setup
the program gave you?!
[EBIHARA]
That's absolutely correct!
I'm impressed you were
able to see the truth
when everyone in the studio has
been fooled this entire time!
You witnessed it all happen
here, ladies and gentleman!
A true psychic has
just been revealed!
My name's Suzuo Fukuda
and I'm with the
Mongolian Spot Agency!
Wow, that was some
brilliant acting!
Thank you very much, sir!
You totally had me
fooled! Good job!
[EBIHARA]
Mogi, you haven't chimed in yet.
What do ya think?
What do I think?
I guess I really only have
one question for him.
What was that "exorcism"
crap all about?
What exactly were
you doing to a spirit
that didn't even exist?
Have any response to that?
Our viewers are wondering
the very same thing, I'm sure.
[REIGEN]
Hm.
Could it be that you
have no spiritual powers?
[REIGEN groans]
[JODO] Come, now.
You shouldn't say that.
All psychics have
different methods.
Excellent work by the
way, Master Jodo!
It should've been
completely obvious
if the boy was possessed or not.
For any true psychic, that is.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
It's not as if I'm referring
to Reigen when I say that.
I'm sure he was simply
trying to liven things up
a bit for the sake
of the program.
[EBIHARA] I assure you,
we didn't ask him to do that.
[SATAKE]
What? It wasn't that, either?
Then why hurt poor Fukuda?
So it was basically
torture, then.
[JODO] What exactly were
you doing up there
for 30 minutes?
Some new kind of dance?
[EBIHARA, AUDIENCE laughs]
Well, it certainly
appeared the boy
was possessed by a spirit.
So I exorcised it.
Even if his spirit
possession was just an act,
real ones can appear
at any moment.
[JODO]
What? An evil spirit was here?
I didn't even notice.
When did it appear?
About 30 minutes ago?
[JODO] Oh! I had no idea
they were so punctual!
[AUDIENCE laughs]
What was it? Huh?
What kind of evil spirit?
It was a...
...a man... I think
he was German...
[REIGEN]
Just stop talking, you idiot!
Don't say another word!
Beethoven.
[JODO]
♪ Du-du-du-dunnn! ♪
[GUY 07A] Did you watch
Supernatural Detective?
[GIRL 07A]
I did! I laughed so hard!
[GUY 07A]
Destroyed on live TV.
[GUY 07B]
That dude was hilarious!
Oh, man. He dug himself
into a hole this time.
There's just no way
that guy's a fraud.
[RITSU] Whoa. How's he gonna
get out of this one?
There's a group of
his victims forming.
Wanna check it out?
We're not exactly
"victims," though.
So he was a con
artist after all.
I bet it's his fault we aren't
getting any job offers.
I knew it. There was
somethin' off about him.
I'm gonna post about even
more of his bullcrap!
Hey, correct me if I'm wrong...
...but isn't the place you work
called the Spirits and Such
Consultation Office?
--Right.
--[INUKAWA] Wait a minute,
would your master's name
happen to be... Reigen Arataka?
Yeah. Why do you ask?
Holy crap, you mean
you haven't heard?
Your master's getting
bashed like crazy
on TV and the Internet!
It's pretty bad, man!
Oh...
We're getting a lot more
actual, paying jobs lately.
If this keeps up and
brings me a little fame,
maybe it'll catapult me
to other platforms.
It's okay. That was
all part of his plan.
[TV GUY 07C]
I know, right?
Did he really think people
wouldn't find out?
And he calls himself
a spirit medium?
[TV LADY 07A] I've actually
been a victim of spiritual
fraud myself.
They said they needed to undress
to perform an exorcism.
Damn! I was set up!
Screw those conniving bastards!
Using me as a scapegoat to boost
their ratings for 30 seconds?!
And that devious old fossil!
I need to work on
containing this as much
as I can so I don't become
an even bigger meme.
Gah! Busted!
[REIGEN]
So it's like that, huh?
You think I'd let
a bunch of little punks
who don't know a thing
about hard work
get the best of me?!
[NARRATOR] But the title
and reputation of the
"scam artist psychic"
spread across
media platforms like wildfire.
In three days' time,
the name "Reigen Arataka"
had become synonymous
with "ultimate evil."
[REIGEN]
Seriously?!
That crap isn't true at all!
How dare these tabloid
jackasses spread
these lies about me?!
[REIGEN]
So here's the plan.
I'd like all of you
guys to talk about
how I solve problems so everyone
will stop calling me a fraud.
Just tell the media
how I helped you.
Huh?
Hey... What's the problem?
Why so quiet?
Just get out of here.
Your lies won't fool us anymore.
[REIGEN]
Huh?
You can't seriously
think that I would--!
[BAR CUSTOMER 06B]
You probably thought people
like us were "prime
targets," didn't you?!
We're not fallin' for that!
[BAR CUSTOMER 06B]
And here I thought he was
kind of cute, too!
[REIGEN]
Well, that tanked.
Guess the only thing
I can do now
is wait until this
all blows over.
Whoa, what the heck?
Are they actually
staking out my place?
There he is! Reigen Arataka!
Oh, god...!
--[REPORTER 07A] Don't run away!
--[REPORTER 07B] Hey!
[REPORTER 07A]
What was that so-called exorcism
you performed on TV?
[REPORTER 07B] Don't you
think you owe it to the public
to explain yourself?
[REPORTER 07C]
At least give us some answers!
[REPORTER 07D]
Is this your day off or what?
[REPORTER 07E] The people aren't
gonna be satisfied with this!
[REPORTER 07A]
Listen, everyone's watching you.
[REPORTER 07B]
You can't run from this forever!
[REPORTER 07A] How about
holding a press conference?
[REIGEN]
Huh?
A press conference?
[NEWSCASTER 07A] Reigen
Arataka, the man allegedly
conning people with
psychic scams...
...announced he'll be holding
a press conference tomorrow.
We believe he'll address
whether or not his
previous activities
were indeed illegal, and if
he actually even possesses
--spiritual powers.
--[MOB] Wow...
[REIGEN] Oh, man...
It'll be morning soon.
[REPORTER 07F]
There he is!
[REPORTER 07G]
Reigen has appeared on stage!
[camera shutters clicking]
[REIGEN]
Damn, that's bright.
Crap
I thought I'd have
a chance if we were
just gonna argue about things,
but now my head's
completely blank.
Okay, calm down.
Start off by trying to make a
better impression of yourself.
[REIGEN] Uh, first,
I'd like to thank you all
for gathering here.
Why are you here, anyway?
[REIGEN]
Then again, sometimes you just
get tired of all this.
[REPORTER 07H]
What's with that attitude?!
[REPORTER 07I]
What?!
Are you mocking us?!
You're the one who said
you'd hold a press conference!
That's 'cause you guys
stalked me everywhere I went.
You basically forced me
into having this thing.
I have a few
questions regarding
some of the fraudulent
acts you've committed.
Hang on a second.
By "fraudulent acts,"
do you mean my business?
Is there anyone here
who can prove
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that I don't have
any spiritual powers?
Or maybe any victims
who can prove
they've been swindled?
There are many people
who've reported
that you scammed them.
Right, self-proclaimed
"victims".
What do you mean by
"self-proclaimed," huh?!
[REIGEN] I mean none
of that has been proven.
Unless and until they do,
I can still call
myself a psychic.
I'm not a criminal.
You should be more careful
with how you phrase things.
I have a question, then.
Go ahead.
[REPORTER 07M] Do you actually
have spiritual powers?
I have no comment on that.
Why won't you
answer the question?
[REIGEN] Because you won't be
satisfied unless I say "no."
And I can't prove
I have spiritual powers
since you all lack
them yourselves.
Are you seriously going to try
and talk your way
out of this mess?
Judging by what you did on
the broadcast the other day,
you do seem like an
excellent ad-libber.
[REPORTERS laugh]
Tch.
[REPORTER 07K] Excuse me.
Did you just click your tongue?
Not at all. I was only
testing the mics.
Uh-oh, looks like he's
copping an attitude.
This guy's finished.
[REPORTER 07L]
When did you start this
psychic business of yours?
About four years ago.
[REPORTER 07N] And what were
you doing prior to that?
I held a job at some company.
[REPORTER 07N]
Did that company have anything
to do with psychics?
[REIGEN]
Nope. Not at all.
[REPORTER 07O] He's actually
answering the questions.
[REPORTER 07P]
What kind of problems did people
come to you with?
[REIGEN]
Stiff shoulders, spirit photos,
and that sort of thing.
[REPORTER 07P]
Any results on those cases?
They've all been solved.
Is there a particular case
that you feel really stands out?
[REIGEN] Getting rid
of some urban legends.
[REPORTER 07L]
Have you ever had any conflicts
with your clients?
[REIGEN]
None.
[REPORTER 07J]
Have you ever sold any expensive
salt or prayer beads?
I have not.
[REPORTER 07K]
Some information about
when you were a
student is spreading
over the Internet.
[REIGEN]
That doesn't matter.
According to your
graduation essay,
you had some plans
for the future.
"I want to be someone."
[REPORTER 07K]
Was "fame" the reason you got
into the psychic business?
Who could say...
Easy, Reigen. 'Cause you're
looking pretty pale.
Stop. Don't keep making the
media outlets your enemy.
Look at him. He's at
a loss for words.
[RITSU]
Something's wrong.
He doesn't seem like himself.
Great Master Reigen...
What's wrong with him?
[REIGEN] Why did I decide
to live my life as a psychic?
It's not like there's
a lot of money in it.
And it's usually a pain.
Thinking back on it,
there was once a time I
did everything efficiently
and was filled with
curiosity about everything.
But then I got bored,
quit my job,
and rented that
office on a whim.
I ended up getting into
this facade of a job
'cause of an ad I
saw in a magazine.
That's right.
I actually meant to quit
this a long time ago.
[REIGEN]
Thanks so much! I appreciate it!
My body felt so heavy,
but now I'm fine!
[laughs]
[REIGEN]
Man, I'm bored.
As it stands, I'm just
a glorified masseuse.
Ugh. Time to throw in the towel.
[REIGEN]
What should I try next?
Being a PI sounds pretty fun.
But I've heard they
mostly do investigations
on cheating spouses.
[door creaks]
[MOB]
'Scuse me.
I saw your sign and
thought I'd stop by.
Sure. C'mon in.
So how may I...?
Oh, it's just a kid.
All right, young man.
So, what do you want?
[MOB]
Well... Um, I'm an esper.
Huh?
[MOB] There are times when
I can't control my powers
too well, and it
gets kinda scary.
[REIGEN]
You little brat.
I'm not in the mood for pranks.
Lemme guess.
Did somebody tell you
to come here and say that to me?
No.
I haven't talked about
this with anyone.
I saw your sign
and thought you might
have the same kind of abilities.
If I tried, I could
see spirits, too.
[REIGEN]
A pathological liar?
Or an overactive
imagination, maybe?
Either way, it seems
like this is something
that's really bothering him.
Well, come on in.
Sure.
I was troubled back when
I was a little kid, too.
Huh?
[REIGEN]
What's with him?
He's staring at me and his eyes
are brimming with hope.
He's serious.
This kid's in his
own fantasy world.
I'll just say something
to get him to go home.
Listen.
Just because you have
these psychic powers
and abilities, it doesn't
mean you're any less
of a human than anyone else.
There are people who are fast,
people who are book smart,
and people with
strong body odor.
Psychic powers
are just like that:
another characteristic.
You must embrace
that characteristic
as a part of yourself and
continue to live positively.
After all, the truth behind
one's charm is kindness.
So, just be a good
person. You got it?
So, may I come by
and talk to you again?
Yeah, I'm not so
sure about that.
I'm pretty busy, you know?
Anyway, you should go
home for today-- Hot!
Move! You'll get burned!
Hey. You said...
You said you could see
ghosts, too, didn't you?
Do you know how
to exorcise them?
[REIGEN]
All right. Come again, tomorrow.
Same time, okay?
Yeah? Really?
I'll show you exactly
how to use your powers.
[REIGEN] Back then,
I couldn't help but admire
this little kid that
walked into my life.
But I wanted something
for myself, too.
I wanted to become
someone special.
Yet this is the result.
I haven't changed
at all since that day.
I just kept using him.
Over and over.
In the end, I couldn't
become anything.
And by using Mob,
all I really did
was hold him back from
enjoying being a kid.
Man, I said some really
terrible things to him.
He wanted to change
and be more social.
And I just tried to cage him in.
[REIGEN]
Hey... Mob...
Are you watching?
You've grown up
so much. You know?
[REPORTER 07R]
That doesn't answer anything!
[REPORTER 07S]
You're wasting our time!
[REPORTER 07T] What was all
that silence all about?
[REPORTER 07L]
Who was that message to?
[REPORTER 07U]
We don't understand!
[REPORTER 07V]
Answer us!
[REPORTER 07L]
It's an earthquake!
[REPORTER 07W]
We're experiencing an extremely
powerful earthquake!
Where're they holding
this thing, anyway?
[REPORTER 07X yelps]
[REPORTER 07Y]
Our cameras!
I-Impossible. Is
Reigen doing this?!
Telekinesis?!
Whoa! What power!
There's something you
don't see every day.
Holy crap. This is
getting serious.
Brother! Hey, brother!
[REPORTER 07Z]
What's with you?!
How can you stay
so calm up there?!
[REPORTER 07W] Are you
the one behind all this?!
Please! You have
to do something!
Are your spiritual
powers doing this?
Goodness. Wonder what's
goin' on around here.
[REPORTER 07L]
Stop this! I beg you!
[REPORTER 07W]
What the hell is this?!
[REIGEN] You done asking
me if I'm a fraud?
[REPORTER 07L screams]
In that case, I think
it's time to end
this press conference.
[REPORTER 07AA]
Hey! Hold on!
[REPORTER 07BB]
What's going to happen to us?!
Dunno.
You should probably concentrate
on finding your next big story.
[REPORTER 07CC]
One of the lights fell!
What the hell just happened?
Such bullcrap...
[REIGEN]
So... Why'd you come here?
Just because.
[DIMPLE]
Let's get the hell outta here.
They'll be runnin'
around for a while.
[inhales]
[REIGEN]
Hey.
Did you know?
[MOB]
Know what?
[REIGEN]
What I really am.
I mean, what they've
been saying in the news.
[MOB] I always have.
From the very beginning.
[REIGEN gasps]
I've known that my
master is genuinely...
...a good guy.
[REIGEN gasps]
[REIGEN]
I am starving.
Let's get some ramen
and head home.
[MOB]
Sure.
Oh, by the way, Master.
I know I'm late but...
Happy Birthday.
[REIGEN]
Mob's finally telling Tsubomi
how he really feels about her?
And he's trying to place
in the top ten of a marathon?
Well, looks like he's
gonna need my help.
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II episode eight:
"Even Then ~Continue Forward~."
First-press limited edition?
Absolute best decision.