Wait up. Wait up!
Be careful, now! You'll
fall if you keep running!
Whoa, are you okay, brother?
[MOM]
See? I tried to warn you.
Come on, let me take a look.
[sobs]
Wow.
Oh, not this again. Shige, stop!
[laughs]
Aw, well, what the heck?
[MEZATO]
Who'd've thought?
A whole building in
Mob's name. Way to go.
Though the Psycho Helmet
Religion still hasn't
found its leader, it now
has over 700 members.
Thanks to an anonymous donation,
they were able to
create a headquarters,
and its followers
work tirelessly
to recruit new people.
They have no form of scripture,
nor any idea what to do.
All they know is that
their beloved founder
is apparently a real esper
and in middle school.
The faith is also
gaining popularity
and spreading on the internet
as a "meme religion."
If Mob ever decides
to appear and make
his identity known, this
order will get even bigger!
I wanna see that happen!
Because...
Well, it just seems
like it'd be fun.
[KOGA] It's your favorite
time of year once again.
That's right, you guessed
it: Annual Marathon time!
[STUDENT 08A]
Aw, man. Seriously?
Enough. No excuses.
Don't even think about
faking an illness!
[MEZATO]
Hey, Mob...
[MOB]
Mezato... What is it?
Well, there's something
I wanna talk to you about.
You think maybe
you could meet me
on the roof during lunch?
It's really important, okay?
I'll be waiting for you.
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo!
Maybe a young lady's going
to ask you out again!
But this time for real!
No, I'm pretty sure
she just wants to talk.
You can be so dramatic, Dimple.
I don't get it.
I liked you much
better when you were
bright-eyed and innocent.
It wasn't that long ago
you'd get beet-red
and flustered from
even talking to a girl.
[MEZATO]
Thanks for coming, Mob.
I wanted to talk to you
about the marathon.
Oh. Right.
Uh-huh, that makes
sense, I guess.
[DIMPLE] Wait... Was he
actually expecting more?
I had an idea about
what you should do.
Why not use your
powers to run faster
and then totally shock
everyone by winning?
But, why?
[MEZATO] W-Well, believe it
or not, there's this "fan club"
that's been looking for you.
Fan club?
[MEZATO]
It's a religious group.
They call themselves
Psycho Helmet.
Oh, it's a religious group.
Those guys...
So during that press
conference the other day...
...apparently there was
a split-second shot
of you from behind.
They analyzed the
footage and found out
that your uniform was
from Salt Middle School.
The followers are positive that
the poltergeist
incident was real,
and it only deepened
their devotion.
Knowing them, they're
sure to observe the area
during the marathon.
When they do, you can
reveal your powers
and then prove you're the leader
they've been looking for!
Don't you wanna make
an important moment
like that as epic as possible?
I'm sorry, but I think
that would be cheating.
Physical strength only.
I'm jogging now,
so maybe by next year
I'll be able to place
in the top ten.
Oh, wow...
You really thought about
this race that much?
Who knew you actually
had a goal in mind?
Ugh! It can't be next year!
Then we'll be cramming for our
high school entrance exams!
Which means we won't
have time to deal
with stuff like this anymore!
Right, I forgot.
That's not good.
What now?
I had a plan.
If I ran in next
year's marathon...
...and placed in the top ten,
I was gonna ask out Tsubomi.
What?! Are you serious?!
Wait, you mean Takane?!
I blew it during the
student council election,
but I was hoping to look cool
placing at next year's marathon.
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo...
How were you able
to change so much
right under my nose
without me noticing?
[MOB] If next year doesn't work,
it'll have to be this year.
I'll just have to
train as hard as I can
and place somewhere
in the top ten.
[INUKAWA laughs]
No way!
I never imagined I'd
hear you say that!
Do you even remember where
you finished last year?
I was 291st...
Right! Way too slow!
You finished in the
very bottom ten of 300!
How do you expect to
jump to the top end
in just ten days?
A 5K is a tough race no
matter how you look at it.
My older brother is
on the high school
track team and he's really good!
Should I ask him for some tips?
Last-minute advice
isn't going to suddenly
turn him into a speedster!
Maybe watch what you eat between
now and the race and
tone your body a bit.
We're not talking
about a diet here!
I know.
Why don't you buy some
fancy running shoes?
He's not made of money.
I'll just do my best.
[ONIGAWARA]
Damn straight, Kageyama!
That's why you're
our shadow leader!
These methods and
their efficiency
don't count for squat!
What really matters is whether
or not you wanna do this!
For you, it's about having
the will to succeed.
However, Kageyama,
doing your best
and giving something your
all ain't exactly easy!
Do you have what
it takes to really
put everything on the line here?
Uh. Yes, I do.
Then take my running shoes.
What? But those shoes
are brand new!
You're just gonna
give them to Mob?
[MOB]
Thanks, but why, Onigawara?
Heh. Just do this thing.
He's the coolest...
[GODA]
Ah, there they are!
[ALL gasp]
So you ended up
with them, Kageyama!
Onigawara bought those
shoes in the wrong size!
[GODA laughs]
[TOME]
Why did you have to ruin it?
[REIGEN] Why are you
so fidgety today, Mob?
[MOB]
Oh, sorry.
I'm just trying to
get in some exercise
every chance I can.
Guess that's not
exactly "fidgeting."
[DIMPLE] The boy's got
a big marathon coming up.
A big marathon, huh?
I always faked being sick
to get out of running them.
He hopes that placing
in the top ten
will give him the courage
to tell Tsubomi how he feels.
[REIGEN gasps]
Seriously?!
That's a big step.
[REIGEN]
Hm...
[REIGEN] You won't be needed
here for the next few days.
Huh? I won't? But why?
[REIGEN] Looks like it's
gonna be a slow week
for new clients.
More importantly,
you should be jogging
to better prepare for this race.
All right, get changed.
Huh?
[REIGEN] We're gonna get
your legs accustomed
to the actual course
you'll be running.
[DIMPLE] Come on!
Lift those feet, Reigen!
Shut up!
I haven't been running
that much myself lately!
I can't hear you! Run!
[REIGEN] Hey, Mob.
You wanna stop for some tea?
We've only been going for
about ten minutes, Master.
Huh? Brother?
Yo! How goes it, Ritsu?
[RITSU] Hey, Dimple. Is he
training for the marathon?
Yeah.
He's gonna place in the top ten
to boost his courage
and ask out Tsubomi.
[RITSU]
What?!
Tsubomi Takane?
I remember playing with her
when we were all little kids.
But honestly, I found her
kinda hard to deal with.
I remember her going
home in the middle
of a game of hide-and-seek...
[inhales] Now I'm worried.
Just be careful with
all of this, brother.
[MOM] Shige! Wash your
own dishes, all right?
Shige!
[RITSU]
It's okay, Mom.
I'll take care of it.
You don't have to, Ritsu.
You shouldn't spoil your
older brother like that.
Is something goin' on?
He's just been workin'
really hard lately.
Knowing that, I don't mind
helping him out a little.
Thanks again for comin'
by today, you two.
I look forward to
working with ya.
I'm just doing this
for my brother.
I want him to be able to
concentrate on training.
That said, we're here
to sub in for Kageyama.
Whatever you need, we're on it.
I appreciate it.
Could you sort those files?
And also, take a look at any
exorcism request emails.
[door creaks]
Excuse me? Are you guys open?
I didn't make an
appointment, so--
[REIGEN]
Oh, you're in luck!
Uh, please, have a seat.
I'll be right with you.
All right. Now, would you mind
getting some tea ready?
And, uh...
Hey. Where'd he go?
He's hiding for some reason.
[RITSU]
Takane?! What is she doing here?
I don't care about myself,
but I can't let her
find out that my brother
has anything to do
with a shady place like this!
Um, I heard that
you also specialize
in relationship advice...
Right?
[TSUBOMI]
Mm-hm.
Think you could do that for us?
[RITSU]
Relationship advice?!
[REIGEN]
Of course!
Just fill out this
questionnaire, please.
Yeah, sure.
[REIGEN]
I see... Mm-hm, mm-hm...
So you go to Salt Middle School.
What a coincidence!
I know someone at
Salt Middle School!
[RITSU] Dammit, Reigen!
You shut your mouth!
So tell us, what's
this person like, Miki?
[REIGEN clears throat]
I appreciate the help, kid,
but I can handle it from here.
I see...
So the person of interest
is probably in your grade.
Maybe a bit older.
And they likely play
some kind of sport.
Oh, wow! You're right!
[REIGEN]
Hm.
I see now...
He's on the soccer
team, so you wanna
get him some new cleats.
But if you get him
a really nice pair,
you're afraid that
the monetary value
may leave a bigger impression
than your feelings.
In that case, I think you
should start off as friends.
Ask him what his hobbies
are outside of soccer...
[REIGEN]
So basically...
...what I'm saying is
that there's no need
for you to rush into things
by asking him out, Miki.
Not in my opinion, at least.
Wow! Okay, thank you so much!
That's actually some
really helpful advice!
Um, I didn't fill out
the questionnaire,
but would you mind
if I asked you
some questions, too?
Sure, no problem!
Is this about a
relationship as well?
Yes.
The person I like
is actually someone
I met at cram school.
[REIGEN]
Ah, that's interesting...
[TSUBOMI]
We talk to each other...
Hey, what's up with you, man?
Sometimes, we even meet up
and walk home together
after cram school.
You think I should
ask this person out?
[RITSU]
Gah!
[REIGEN] Hm... Well, considering
you two are already close,
I think it'd be fine to ask
them out as soon as you like.
[RITSU]
Hey!
From what you've been
telling me just now,
the other person is obviously
interested in you, as well.
If you ask them out,
there's a high
probability they'll say yes.
[RITSU]
It's over...
[TSUBOMI]
Okay, then.
[MIKI, TSUBOMI]
Thank you very much.
Feel free to stop by anytime.
Do you know those
two or something?
'Cause they looked
a little older than you.
Well, uh...
[RITSU] I can't tell
Brother, I just can't.
[panting]
[RITSU]
I believe in you, Shige!
[MIKI] I didn't know you went
to cram school, Tsubomi.
You've never
mentioned it, before.
I don't.
The truth is, I just made
that whole story up.
I didn't want you to get
scammed or something,
so I thought I'd throw him
a curve ball and test him a bit.
You what?!
That's crazy, but it
makes sense, I guess.
So what do you think?
Did he pass your
little test or what?
[TSUBOMI]
Hm...
How should I put this...?
[TSUBOMI] He didn't say
anything wrong, exactly.
So, he's probably fine.
You can do it!
My parents came out for this.
Who do you think is the fastest?
[MEZATO]
This day has finally arrived.
It looks like there are
a few Psycho Helmet
followers waiting
near the finish line.
It's time to present
their beloved leader.
[MEZATO]
Come on, Mob! You've got this!
Ritsu will be just fine,
but I'm worried about Shigeo.
Yeah, he's got the
stamina of a snail.
We should watch from
somewhere mid-course
rather than the finish line.
[KIJIBAYASHI coughs]
Oh, no. I think I've
caught a cold. Bummer.
[INUKAWA coughs]
Oh, did you catch a cold,
too, Kijibayashi?
So did I!
[KIJIBAYASHI] Wow, that's
such a coincidence, Inukawa.
[SARUTA coughs]
[KIJIBAYASHI]
You, too, Saruta?
Not bad for a first-year.
[SARUTA]
Oh, thank you, you're too kind.
The Telepathy Club's
really taught me a lot.
[TOME] You're running,
you lazy bastards!
Even Mob's lined up
to do this thing!
So you three better
get going, too!
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo!
Hey, how ya doin', kid?
Uh?
[DIMPLE] He's doomed.
The poor guy is super nervous.
Don't look so down, Kageyama!
[MOB]
President.
Show everybody what
all that training
has done for you.
We're your rivals
out there today!
[MOB]
Rivals...
I'll do my best!
[ONIGAWARA] Heh. Looks like
he put those to good use.
Way to go, shadow leader.
[PE TEACHER]
We will now begin the boys' race
of the Salt Middle
School Marathon.
Get ready!
[PE TEACHER]
On your marks!
Set!
[RITSU]
Brother!
That leg's gonna keep you from
catching up to the frontrunners.
Do ya want me to possess you?
You only need to make
the top ten, right, Mob?
Suit yourself.
My kid fell far behind
and he looked so annoyed.
[MOM 08B] There's no way
they'll catch up to the front.
Ritsu passed by a long time ago.
Yeah...
--[DAD gasps]
--[MOM] Shige!
[MOM] Oh, no! What
happened to your leg?!
You've been building up
your stamina, right?
Hang in there!
Just keep it up! You're
doing great, Shigeo!
I feel so proud of him.
Me, too.
I should make
something extra yummy
for dinner tonight.
[TSUBOMI]
There's Mob.
You can do--
[DIMPLE]
His form's all wrong.
Did he sprain something?
His pace is getting
erratic, too.
Hey! You've only got
about a kilometer to go.
Move those legs!
Hey, Reigen! Nice
outfit there, buddy!
Shut it.
I thought I'd show up, step in,
and help him keep his pace
towards the end of the run...
...but the group of guys
up front are way too fast.
They're so far ahead.
I'm not sure you'd catch up
even if you sprinted.
I've been counting the runners.
He's currently in 74th place.
And I am really proud of him
for doing that well...
...but for him to finish
in the top ten,
he has to pass 64 others.
That's a problem.
Should we get a taxi?
[REIGEN] I mean, the thought
did cross my mind, but...
Don't be ridiculous.
Look at that face.
See? He hasn't given up yet.
[panting]
[KOGA]
Kageyama. You're finally awake.
You shouldn't try pushing
yourself too far.
[MOB]
Yes, sir.
So I take it the
marathon's over, right?
It is.
Your younger brother
managed to overtake
some upper classmen and
ended up in 9th place.
He did, huh?
That's awesome.
Kageyama.
You know, you used to
always seem so down to me.
But you seem happier lately.
Yeah?
[KOGA]
Do you need a ride home?
[MOB]
No, that's okay. Thanks.
He didn't show...
[FOLLOWER 08H]
Yeah...
Where in the world
is our leader?
[MOM humming]
You're in a good mood.
And I have every reason to be!
We're celebrating!
Ritsu placed 9th and
Shige did his best!
[DAD]
Fair enough!
--[DAD laughs]
--[doorbell rings]
Huh?
I'll get it.
It might be Shige.
[MOM] Mr. Koga just called
saying he left school
a little while ago.
[RITSU] I'm glad it
was only mild anemia.
What's up?
I know you.
You're that kid from--
How did you find this place?
Didn't I tell you
I'd be seeing you again?
[MOM]
Who is it? Friend of yours?
[RITSU]
Mom, wait!
Don't come over here right now!
Easy. No need to be so rude.
Looks like your
parents are here.
How unfortunate.
That complicates things.
Hold on. What is that
supposed to mean?
[gasps]
[MOB]
What's that?
Looks like smoke.
Wonder what's going
on over there.
A fire, I guess?
Uh-- Wait!
Isn't that about where...?
[LADY 08A] Apparently,
there was a sudden explosion
and it just went up in flames.
[LADY 08B] They said
it might've been arson.
No one's seen the family,
so we don't know if
they got to safety or--
[LADY 08B] Oh, you're one
of the Kageyama boys.
Thank goodness.
We were so worried.
Hey! Hold on!
What are you doing?!
[LADY 08B]
Get away from there!
[LADY 08A] Someone, please!
Stop him before he--!
[LADY 08C screams]
[LADY 08A]
He walked right into the fire!
[MOB] It's okay. They're fine.
Dad was home today.
He can be kinda
strict at times...
...but he's strong and reliable.
He even took the day
off from work today
to watch me run.
And Mom...
She's always extra careful
when she uses the stove.
When I was younger,
she yelled at me
for messing around
with fireworks.
Not to mention, Ritsu was here.
My brilliant younger brother
who always keeps a cool head.
It's all right.
It'll be all right.
It's too bad our home
is burning down, but...
...as long as we're together,
we can start over.
[MOB]
So no one's here?
Good! They must've
gotten away, then!
[DIMPLE]
Shigeo!
There were signs of a
struggle at the front door.
It looks like somebody
forced their way inside!
Then this was done on purpose?
Wait! If somebody broke in...
...then that same person
could've kidnapped
them and taken them away!
Oh, no! I have to hurry
and look for clues!
[gasps]
[DIMPLE]
Close your eyes, Shigeo!
Look away! Look away!
[yells]
[REIGEN] The super dangerous
esper organization,
Claw, attacks Seasoning City!
The boss, minions, all of them!
It appears that I,
Reigen Arataka,
must make a stand against
them once again!
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode nine:
"Show Me What You've Got
~Band Together~."
Illegal downloads?
You wanna be cursed?