[TERUKI]
Well, whattaya know...?
Looks like you're
the last man standing.
Damn it! Stupid brats!
Who do you think you are?!
[HOSHINO]
Dust Cyclone!
[ASAHI]
Flamethrower!
[HOSHINO, ASAHI]
Combo Attack!
Telekinetic Pillar of Flame!
This was nothing!
You shouldn't underestimate me--
[groans]
Way to go, you two. Good job.
You've gotten stronger.
We've been practicing every day.
It's all thanks to what
you taught us, Teru.
We appreciate
the help, Takeuchi.
[TAKEUCHI]
There's no need to thank me.
I defected from the
organization as well.
[TERADA] And I acted
like I betrayed you
to launch a surprise attack.
Good thing I can
think on my feet
and not fold during
an intense situation.
[TERADA]
I think-- Hey, what the--?
--Why can't I move?
--[TERUKI] Kaito.
[KAITO]
Lie-Detection Telepathy!
Everything's okay.
He hasn't betrayed us yet.
Hey, whattaya mean by "yet"?!
So, what should we do now?
Reigen said we didn't have
to fight these guys head on,
but I'm beginning
to think otherwise.
We have to take our city back.
[BOSS]
Pathetic dogs...
They forget how terrifying
their master can be
if he's not there to remind
them every minute.
[BOSS]
Sho is here.
Okay, let's go.
[SHO]
Hey, Ritsu. I'm curious.
Why are you being
so cooperative?
I think it's because
I can relate to what
you're going through.
There are times when I worry
about what would happen
if my brother went
berserk with his powers.
Right now, that's exactly
what your father's doing.
And you're probably the only
one who can stop him.
Yeah! I know I can!
I'll show you that
I can finish this!
[SHO gasps]
There he is...
It's Shimazaki!
[RITSU]
I can tell just by looking...
He's really strong!
[SHO] He's a teleporter who can
read his enemy's movements.
--I think we should--
--[RITSU] You go on ahead.
I'll stay behind
and keep him busy.
You can't handle
'im on your own.
He's one of the strongest
in the whole organization.
That's why I'm staying.
In return, you've gotta promise
me you'll stop your father.
All right, you have my word.
I sure am glad to
have you around.
[RITSU]
Go!
[SHO grunts]
[RITSU grunts]
[RITSU]
Where'd he go?
[gasps]
[RITSU gasps]
[RITSU] Guess he's
not gonna follow Sho...
[SHIMAZAKI]
Looking for me?
Listen, I'd appreciate it if
you wouldn't resist so much.
Bullying the weak isn't
exactly my style.
[RITSU] Don't flatter yourself.
You're as weak as I am!
[SHIMAZAKI]
Oh yeah?
You're about to find out
just how wrong you are.
[RITSU grunts]
[SHO] I should've taken him out
way before it got to this point.
But, I was so powerless
I couldn't do anything
but sit back and watch...
[HATORI]
That's far enough.
Such a shame to come
all this way for nothing.
Now you'll have to deal with me.
[SHO] My dad uses his
abilities for evil.
I'm going to use mine
to show him what's right!
[SHO]
I'll put an end to this!
[MOB] How awful. Someone did
this with their psychic powers?
[DIMPLE] They're using that
tower as their base.
Reigen and the others
should be here, soon.
[glass shatters]
Hey. Some brat just walked up.
Too scared to run?
[CLAW MEMBER 11C] I grabbed
some good stuff for dinner!
Now they're looting.
[MOB] I've gone to that
store with Ritsu before.
[MOB] Put back what you took.
Stealing's a crime.
--You should know better.
--Who the hell are you, kid?
[CLAW MEMBER B laughs]
[CLAW MEMBER A]
Don't you watch the news?
This town belongs to us now.
[CLAW MEMBER C laughs] Yo! Easy!
You're gonna traumatize him.
Listen to me.
You shouldn't do this.
Don't use your powers this way.
--Stop.
--[CLAW MEMBERS grunt]
No, he couldn't be.
Is this kid a natural esper?
[MOB] Tell me... Could you
guys manufacture this can?
[CLAW MEMBER A]
Huh?
Could you actually plant
and grow the vegetables
in this sandwich?
Or fix that glass
door you broke?
Could psychic powers... help you
come up with a useful invention?
Or heal someone who's sick?
What're you trying to say?!
[MOB] Sorry, but you guys
are making a huge mistake.
You believe you're special
just because of your
psychic abilities.
None of you would be able
to survive on your own.
Not without the help of others.
[CLAW MEMBER C]
Whatever, jackass!
As long as you have power, you
can make anyone submit to you!
Oh, that reminds me...
Never use your powers
against others.
If you haven't come across
someone who can show you why...
...then allow me.
[DIMPLE] Crap! He's pissed.
I'm gonna get back.
[CLAW MEMBER D]
He's making a move!
[CLAW MEMBER E]
Gather everyone up!
[MINEGISHI]
Well, well...
Looks like we had quite the
stray show up at our doorstep.
Minegishi!
I'll take him down.
You guys back me up.
[MOB gasps]
[MINEGISHI] These things
will keep growing forever
as long as I give
them enough energy.
On top of that, I can
make as many as I want.
[MOB grunts]
Guess you can do it, too.
[MOB] Seems to me... you don't
really like plants, do you?
[MINEGISHI] That's right.
They're nothing but tools.
[CLAW MEMBER B]
All right! Drop him!
[CLAW MEMBER C]
Don't let Minegishi down!
[CLAW MEMBER 11A]
Hit him with your telekinesis!
[RITSU grunts]
[SHIMAZAKI] Fighting those more
powerful than you is useless.
You should join our side.
[RITSU]
That might be a little easier.
But, it isn't half as much fun.
[SHIMAZAKI]
Hm...
The difference in our skills
should be obvious by now.
Sure you won't change your mind?
Maybe you just need a
bit more persuasion.
[RITSU] I always wanted to be
able to use psychic powers.
But now that mine
have finally awakened,
I've come to
understand something.
What I really wanted
was to give something
every ounce of energy I had...
To shed all the blood, sweat,
and tears inside me to ensure
I could live a fun life.
I won't let you or
anyone take that away!
Guess you might not be such
a good fit for us after all.
No hard feelings, kid.
Oh, man...
I managed to land a hit on him!
[SHIMAZAKI] My, my. You're more
resilient than I'd imagined.
[SAKURAI] We need to repay
you for what you did.
Guess you're not sewer rats.
You're cockroaches.
[TSUCHIYA] We've changed
since we were in Claw.
[MURAKI] Now that we're
living on our own terms,
you'll find we're much stronger.
[SHIMAZAKI] But that won't
change the outcome.
[TERUKI] Don't act so tough.
We know you're panicking.
You can read our moves,
but at some point,
there'll be too many
of us to keep up with.
It's time for round two!
[TERADA shouts]
[TSUCHIYA]
Takeuchi!
[TAKEUCHI shouts]
[TSUCHIYA grunts]
[TAKEUCHI]
Tsuchiya!
[TAKEUCHI grunts]
[TERUKI grunts]
[KOYAMA]
Not happening, freakshow!
[gasps]
[TERADA grunts]
[SHIMAZAKI]
Aren't you gonna shoot?
[SHIMAZAKI gasps]
[gasps]
[SHIMAZAKI] Trying to pin me
down is a waste of time.
[SAKURAI shouts]
[SHIMAZAKI]
I told you.
[SHIMAZAKI] Nothing you do
will change the outcome.
Hm?
[SHIMAZAKI]
Oh?
[TERUKI] Keep hitting him hard
and fast! The more we do...
...the easier it is to tell
where he'll teleport!
[MOB] They're stronger
than the division guys...
Don't let up, Shigeo!
[CLAW MEMBER F] Yes!
He's scared now! Keep it up!
[CLAW MEMBERS gasp, shout]
[MATSUO] Looks like you're
having some trouble.
[MOB]
Aren't you...?
I'm happy to lend you a
hand with him, if you like.
Go, my children!
[CLAW MEMBER A] It's Matsuo,
the evil-spirit user!
[CLAW MEMBER B] He's gonna
launch a monster-assault on us!
[MINEGISHI]
You shouldn't underestimate me.
--[MATSUO grunts]
--Matsuo!
[MOB gasps]
[CLAW MEMBER A]
What's with the weird bottle?
Talk about bad taste.
[MATSUO]
No! Please! Anything but that!
Even I can't control him!
Don't touch it!
Dumbass.
With Minegishi on our side,
nothing scares us!
[MATSUO gasps]
Huh? What happened?
Why is everyone--?
[MOGAMI groans]
What the hell? What is that?!
[MOB]
Mogami!
Not good.
What happened to him?
[MOGAMI] First, you trap
me in the Poison Jar,
and now you want me
to devour espers.
You're such lowly creatures...
[gasps]
What the hell is that thing?!
[MINEGISHI] My plants!
They aren't listening to me!
[MINEGISHI yells]
[MINEGISHI grunts]
[MOB]
No! Stop!
[MOGAMI]
Why should I?
I've been watching, and none of
these insects deserve to live.
Some people never change,
no matter how many
chances you give them.
But they still might be able to!
Promise you won't do
anything bad ever again!
I-I promise, I won't.
Just spare me, please!
See?!
What if he's just
lying to stay alive?
Are you going to
personally watch over
these people to see if
they've reformed?
Do you think you can keep
an eye on them forever?
[MOB]
Well... no.
But we need to have faith in
one another to get through life.
If we can't do that,
then we'll never get anywhere.
[MOGAMI]
Predictable, coming from you.
But there are things in this
world that can't be solved
with mere kindness.
Sometimes, it's necessary
to be tough on people.
If you can learn to do that,
you will be invincible,
Shigeo Kageyama.
[DIMPLE] Do you think
Mogami disappeared for good
this time, or...?
Be tough on people, huh?
I'm not very good at that.
[SHO] I finally made it here
and Claw's finished, Father!
[BOSS] Sho. Surely,
there's a better way
for us to handle this.
We're family, after all.
What? So now you want
to act like a father?
You've never cared about
a damn thing I did or said.
Should've attacked while
playing the obedient son.
--What a wasted opportunity.
--[growls]
[BOSS] Now don't get
in my way any further.
It took me 20 years
to get to this point.
[SHO]
So what?!
Seeing all those years go down
the drain serves you right!
I'm just as strong
as the Ultimate 5!
Come on! Fight me, man to man!
Don't make me laugh.
You underestimate me.
[SHO] So, you've got a powerful
barrier that activates
when I get too close.
Is that your true power?
In that case...!
[gasps, grunts]
[SHO]
Damn it! He's mocking me!
[gasps]
[BOSS] These techniques
are child's play.
[BOSS]
How disappointing.
I thought you would've grown
a little more than that.
[BOSS] Oh... You've learned
to control the degree of
light refraction around you?
[SHO]
Here's the ace up my sleeve!
Three months' worth of
stored-up energy...
Charge Bomb!
Hell, yeah! Justice prevails!
[gasps]
[SERIZAWA] Really sorry...
Bad time for my bathroom break.
[BOSS]
No, that's all right.
This is just his
rebellious phase.
Misbehaving again?
You won't turn out to be
a decent adult like that.
[SHO] Screw you! That was
three months' worth of energy!
[SERIZAWA] Let's stop
fighting and take over
the world together!
What do you say?
Don't bother.
His mind's made up.
But I understand why Sho
disagrees with what I'm doing.
You fear this plan
will fail, don't you?
Well, that's because
you don't know the truth.
While I was seeking out new
members of Claw, the real
reason I went around the world
was to see if global domination
would actually be possible.
But after my search,
I couldn't find a single esper
stronger than me, anywhere.
I have been bestowed
with the ultimate power.
[SHO] And you think that
somehow gives you the right
to take over the world?
Hear that, Serizawa? He's crazy!
Totally messed up in the head!
President...
You're so cool.
[SHO grunts] Idiots with power
are the worst to deal with!
[BOSS] Your last attack
was quite impressive.
The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
Don't talk like that!
We're not the same!
[BOSS] You said you'd been
charging up energy and saving it
for the past three months?
I have the same ability.
--What?!
--[BOSS] Didn't I tell you?
I've spent the past 20 years
preparing for this moment.
[SHO] You weren't just gathering
troops and scouting around.
You were...!
Would you like to see a little
of what I've been saving up?
--[gunshots]
--[SAKURAI groans]
[SHIMAZAKI] You poor Scars don't
know when to quit, do you?
Just face it. You're outgunned
and outmatched.
[KOYAMA]
Shut it!
You're a damn coward
who doesn't have the guts
to go against the boss!
[SHIMAZAKI chuckles]
The reason he named you "Scars"
is 'cause you're all
disappointments. Failures.
Every one of you was considered
damaged goods from the start.
[KOYAMA growls]
I'll show you "damaged"!
Telekinetic Helix!
[SHIMAZAKI] Even my most
basic abilities as an esper...
...are far more powerful
than all of yours combined.
[SHIMAZAKI]
I'll say it one more time...
Stop resisting and give up.
[gunshots]
[SAKURAI]
You say that, but...
...that manhole cover
hurt just now, didn't it?
[RITSU gasps]
Hey, Teru!
Yeah. So, it looks
like if he can't detect
the attack in advance...
...then he can't stop it.
He's the one who's
been cornered here!
[sighs]
You're are a smart
one, aren't you...?
And that means...
[TERUKI grunts]
[glass shattering]
...you'll be the first to die.
But, you won't be the last.
[TERUKI gasps]
[yells]
[SHIMAZAKI yells]
[TSUCHIYA]
This is bad. He'll kill him.
What can we do?
Enough. It's time to end this.
--[gasps]
--[TERUKI] Next, from behind!
How'd you--?!
[TERUKI] It might
be convenient to be able
to read your opponents' moves...
...but it makes your own
movements really simplistic.
You rely too much
on your powers.
[grunts, yells]
[SHIMAZAKI]
Well, I'm shocked.
'Cause other than the boss...
...the world's greatest
esper is yours truly.
[laughs]
Don't flatter yourself!
There are people in
this world with abilities
you can't even fathom.
You're not that special at all.
I mean, even I could defeat you.
Why you--
[grunts]
[RITSU] You're right!
It's when he's distracted!
[TERUKI]
Nice one! Way to go, Ritsu!
[TSUCHIYA grunts]
Fifth Punch!
[TAKEUCHI]
Super Destructive Energy Blast!
[SHIMAZAKI grunts]
[SHIMAZAKI groans]
[SHIMAZAKI]
Get a hold of yourself...
[KOYAMA bellows]
[SHIMAZAKI]
Y-You need to focus...
Just concentrate and
you'll figure everything out.
Everyone here is an esper.
Ignore everything but them...
Concentrate. Concentrate...
Mind's Eye!
[SHIMAZAKI] There's nothing
you can do that will
ever work on me again.
Your injuries, the weaknesses
you're not even aware of yet...
Your blurred vision...
I can see through
anything and everything.
It's too late to
have any regrets.
[SHIMAZAKI gasps]
[TERUKI]
What's wrong?
[SHIMAZAKI]
It feels like...
...something with tremendous
energy is heading this way.
I'm pretty sure I know
who that would be.
I guess you finally woke up...
...Kageyama.
[SHIMAZAKI laughs]
You're kidding, right?
Let's see whose abilities
could possibly be greater!
[chuckles]
Now, come at me,
and I'll face you head-on!
[REIGEN]
Self-Defense Rush!
[NARRATOR] Another one
of Reigen's special moves!
When it's unclear if it's
actually self-defense,
he'll yell out "Self-Defense!"
just to be safe.
[SHIMAZAKI yells]
[SHIMAZAKI] Impossible!
I couldn't sense him at all.
Who is he?!
Hey, Reigen!
[MURAKI] Everyone, get up!
The great master is here!
[SHIMAZAKI] What did he say?
Don't tell me...
There's an esper who can make
every trace of his
presence disappear?
What should I do? Withdraw?
Master. This one is
actually really strong.
So please step back.
I can handle him.
That boy from earlier,
and this unknown esper...
How many are there?
Are they actually
a huge organization?
More importantly, this kid is
on an entirely different level.
Heh.
Look, I give up, okay?
It's not worth
the risk. I'm done.
[REIGEN] Well, that was a lot
easier than I thought it'd be.
What happened to
taking over the world?
The boss is the only
one gunning for that.
As long as I'm having fun,
I don't really care.
[MOB]
As long as you're having fun?
Huh?
You disrupted the lives of
all those people just for that?
Are you serious?
[SHIMAZAKI gasps]
[TERADA]
The little coward ran away!
[KOYAMA] Does that...
even count as a win?
Who knows?
He may strike again.
No, I'm pretty sure
he's gone for good.
After going through that,
he'll probably change
his ways from now on.
Shige.
Ah, Ritsu! You okay?
Yeah.
And Mom and Dad are somewhere
safe and sound, too.
Thank goodness.
It's just like Dimple
and Master said.
[DIMPLE] That was one
hell of a scare, huh...?
[REIGEN]
Ah, shut up...
[TERUKI] I guess all we have
left is the last boss.
Hoshino and the others should
be getting people to safety.
Let's regroup with them
and begin our attack.
[MOB] No. You've all
suffered injuries.
I'll go in alone.
[TERUKI]
Wait... Kageyama!
What are you talking about?!
I wanna go, too!
One of my friends
already went in!
[MOB]
No.
This might be hard to hear,
but you'll just be in my way.
I'm sorry.
[DIMPLE]
"Be tough on people..."
So that's how Shigeo interpreted
what Mogami told him...
Dimple, stay with him.
Yeah, yeah I know...
[DIMPLE] Aren't you scared
to do this on your own?
[MOB]
Of course. But, still...
Having someone else get hurt
scares me even more.
I'm sure I'll figure
something out.
[DIMPLE]
Crap...
I'm trying to take advantage of
him while he's still a kid...
...but Shigeo's going to be
an adult before I know it.
--[clack]
--[MOB] Hmm.
[SERIZAWA]
Damn. You're just a small fry...
Are you even in middle school?
This is a really bad
time for a field trip.
Would you be so kind
as to leave the premises?
[REIGEN] Mob finally infiltrates
the enemy's base.
Can he get past Serizawa
and make it to the boss?
After defeating his son Sho,
the boss reveals
his true identity.
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II, Episode 12:
"The Battle for Social
Rehabilitation ~Friendship~."
Option C: buys Blu-rays,
manga, and event tickets!