[NARRATOR]
The "Spirits and Such" home page
was surprisingly well-received!
That resulted in more and more
new clients with
legitimate requests
for investigations
and exorcisms.
But, in hindsight, some of these
new opportunities were jobs that
never should've been taken
in the first place.
[REIGEN]
A curse, huh...?
Well, that's not exactly
what we do here.
Sorry, but you're gonna have to
ask someone else.
Thanks for comin' in.
You're a psychic, aren't ya?
Come on, buddy,
don't be like that!
I'm begging you!
Slam a curse on this guy!
Yeah, that's not happening.
[CLIENT 03A]
Dammit!
Come all the way down here
and you treat me like this?!
Well, look, we didn't
ask you to come, you know.
[CLIENT 03A] What? How dare
you say that to me!
[MOB]
He's ready to fight...
Okay, okay, I'll do it.
Now don't pop a blood
vessel all over me.
Seriously? I can't
thank you enough!
But only this once, ya got it?
And I won't be held responsible
for what happens.
[gasps]
[CLIENT 03A]
Hmm?
[sighs]
Keep this talisman
with you at all times.
You kidding me?
[REIGEN] Do not shun the
powerful magic, my friend.
If you keep it
with you, someday,
something will happen.
I won't ask for money,
but I will ask that
you tell no one what
took place here today.
[CLIENT 03A]
Look, I believe you.
But if I find out
you're lying...
...then I will put
a curse on you.
[REIGEN sighs]
He's finally gone.
I kind of understand
how it feels
to hate someone so much you'd
wanna curse them, though.
Do you have someone like that?
[REIGEN]
No, not really.
So, what about you?
Someone I wanna curse?
Hmm...
[REIGEN] Hey, you don't have
to think about it that hard.
[REIGEN gasps]
No, I guess not.
Don't do that!
Ya scared the hell outta me!
[MOB] But are you sure
about what you did
with that guy a minute ago?
It's fine, I just made
the whole thing up.
It won't really bother anybody.
[MOB]
Are you certain about that?
I mean... even if it's a lie,
in his mind, he still
managed to put
a curse on somebody.
He might spend
the rest of his life
thinking it's real.
Doesn't the thought
of that... scare you?
Mob?
[REIGEN]
That's pretty rare.
He almost never speaks up
about what he's thinking.
Something about
what happened here
really bothered him.
Am I missing something?
[phone rings]
Spirits and Such
Consultation Office.
[REIGEN]
So this is the place, huh?
[CLIENT 03B]
At first, I just thought
it was some creepy stalker.
So I called the police.
But now... Now I don't
think it's a human at all.
It was there!
I saw it peeking through
the window at me!
Oh, yeah?
[gasps]
[cardboard ripping]
This is the fifth floor,
and there's no veranda.
That is weird.
Dimple, are you here?
Yeah, what's up?
Go take a look outside
at this window.
See if there are any rope
marks on the roof, too.
Why am I helping you again?
If you see any evil spirits,
eat 'em, all right?
Hey, Mob, are you
feelin' anything?
Yes. It's a small
presence, but...
[gasps]
Nothing. I don't see
a damn thing out here.
Hey, don't shut the
window on me, ya jerk!
But everything she's
describing sounds
exactly like a stalker.
Why would a ghost be
interested in a living woman?
You got any insight on this?
No, not really.
It's pretty uncommon for spirits
to have any sexual desire.
We couldn't reproduce
if we wanted to.
[REIGEN] Is sexual desire
always a part of love, though?
I-I really don't wanna
talk about this with you.
Yeah, well that makes
two of us, ya freak.
[yelps]
Hold on. Is this a poltergeist?
What do we do?
Maybe I angered it!
It's throwing a fit because
I called an exorcist here!
Feels like it stopped.
[screams]
Outside the window!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Leave me alone!
[REIGEN]
Mob! Get rid of it!
Wait a minute.
That's a living person!
So it is a stalker!
Damn! The bastard disappeared!
[gasps]
He's in the next apartment!
[REIGEN]
Huh?
[doorbell rings]
[NEIGHBOR mumbling]
Who are these people?
I-I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm sorry I left my
body to peek inside
your apartment, okay?
I couldn't help it.
I fell madly in love
with you at first sight!
[gasps]
[NEIGHBOR] I've never
felt like this before!
I didn't know what to do.
I'm at a loss here.
But either way,
it's gonna happen!
I'm gonna be her boyfriend!
Don't get in my way,
or I'll kill you!
[REIGEN]
Huh?
You, die!
Enough, ya dirty
little Peeping Tom.
[BOTH grunting]
[NEIGHBOR] Violence is
wrong! Don't hurt me!
I'll call the police,
you bastard!
What is this guy's problem?
It was all my fault!
I'll never do it again!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please, forgive me!
My love for you is real,
you gotta believe me!
Please, just... just...
Your love is "real"?
Gimme a break!
It's really creepy,
that's what it is, stalker!
--[gasps]
--[siren blares]
Ugh. Can't believe
I was scared of him.
[REIGEN] He tried to blame
all of his creepy stalking
on a supernatural phenomenon.
Don't get any ideas, kid.
But, why?
[REIGEN]
Hmm?
Why do we treat them
so differently?
It could be a person,
or a spirit...
[REIGEN sighs] Poor Mob's got
a lot on his mind today.
I'll talk to him later.
Okay, guys, let's head on home,
maybe eat some soba.
[yawns]
[MOB]
Okay.
Oh! There they are!
We've been waiting for ya!
They just keep on comin',
one after another.
Three clients in a day.
This internet thing
is pretty awesome.
[STUDENT 03A]
We wanna do something
really unforgettable
before we graduate!
So we thought, like, why
don't we go to a well-known
haunted place and take
a photo together?
[STUDENT 03AA] But we don't
want anything bad to happen.
[REIGEN] They just wanna
have some fun, huh?
Nothin' wrong with that.
All right, when and where?
Right now, dude! We've got
a car parked outside.
[REIGEN] So this is our
future work force, huh?
[REIGEN]
I thought you said we'd be there
in 20 minutes.
It's been over 30.
I meant 20 minutes from
when you last asked me.
[REIGEN]
We might not get that soba.
So are you, like,
his... assistant?
I just work part time.
Part-timing at the exorcist's
office! That's crazy!
[REIGEN]
Mob! Stay focused.
You need to be ready
for anything, understood?
Right.
[STUDENT 03B]
Whoa, sounds serious!
[STUDENTS laugh]
[STUDENT 03A]
We're here.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[STUDENT 03B]
Whoa, this place is freaky!
[STUDENT 03AA]
You guys, I am so excited!
[REIGEN]
Any spiritual activity?
[MOB]
Maybe a little...
[DIMPLE] But not enough to make
this a popular ghost spot.
[REIGEN]
Okay, guys, the coast is clear.
Take that photo.
[STUDENT 03A]
Sure thing.
[STUDENT 03AA]
Get ready! Say, "cheese"!
Wait, would you mind
taking this for us?
[REIGEN] I'd love to say no,
but they're clients, so...
Right. Say, "che--"
[STUDENT 03AA]
Oh! Make sure the flash is on.
Say, "cheese."
[ALL]
Cheese!
All right. Let's go.
My apprentice has
school in the morning.
Sure. Thanks for your help.
--[STUDENT 03AA] Thank you.
--Thanks for everything.
So about my payment: will it
be cash or credit card?
Huh?! Payment?!
Are you bein'
for real right now?
Yes? It was a job.
Nothing happened! Only
thing you did was complain
about the drive
and take a picture!
Do we seriously have to pay you
for all the nothing you did?
That's like, fraud,
or something!
Yeah, fraud or something! Ugh!
[engine revs]
[REIGEN]
So they refused to pay...
...and they're leaving
us out here?
That's just perfect.
So what now?
[REIGEN]
Guess we'll have to get back
to the road and try
calling a taxi.
No soba for us.
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A]
Hey! Hey, kid!
You ignorin' me? Hey!
Stop walkin' so slowly.
You're breakin' my stride, man.
Listen, can I borrow some money?
[MOB]
What? I don't have any.
Why are you so nervous?
Could you bring
some tomorrow, then?
Huh?
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A]
You heard him, punk.
[BOTH cackle]
Sugimoto, what are you--?
Hey! What's wrong?
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03B]
Why the hell are you
taking your clothes off?!
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A giggling]
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A]
I'm an angel!
Sugimoto!
[MOB] Dimple, stop it!
Just leave him alone!
Wh-What's going on?
Have you lost your mind?
What the hell was that?
What happened to me back there?
Let's start this over!
Hey, kid! You were laughin'
at me, weren't you?!
What? No, I wasn't!
Shut up!
Now don't you know
how this works?
I'm bullying you for your mone--
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03B]
Sugimoto!
I'm fine. There's
no need for this.
So just let him go.
Okay, Ritsu?
You sure?
He seems like bad news to me.
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03A gasps]
You're actin' weird today, man.
What's your problem?
You makin' trouble for
one our club members?
Huh?
Hey, who are you people?
Surrounding me, huh?
What's up with that?!
Fine! You wussies want a fight?
I'll kick all your asses!
Hey, don't push me like that!
Get off me!
Whoa! Stop it, I can't
move my arms! Cut it out!
Uh, guys? No need to fight.
I'm fine, okay?
Yeah, you're right.
[HIGH SCHOOLER 03B]
Sugimoto!
We'll get you guys
for this, damn it!
You sure you wanna let 'em go?
[MOB]
Yeah. Thank you, though.
You need to learn you have
to fight back sometimes.
Otherwise, they'll just
bully you even more.
[MOB] But, I can't think
of a way to do that.
You could use your shadow leader
powers and kick their asses.
There's no need
for brother to waste
his abilities on a couple
of thugs like that.
If they come back here,
I can deal with them.
Yeah, punishing the bad guy
could be a good thing
for those boys.
It wouldn't be too bad
for society, either.
Next time, deal with
them yourself.
You have the power to, right?
[REIGEN] A ghost showed up
in your photo, huh?
Yeah.
We're freaked out and not
sure what to do, so...
Just throw some salt around.
I'm not running a
charity service here.
We're sorry about before!
Whatever you want, we'll pay it!
You have my attention.
Look, you can see the
ghost, clear as day.
We want you to go
back to that spot,
find that thing,
and get rid of it!
It's so much easier to just
exorcise the photo itself.
No point in going back...
Yes, there is!
Just knowing something like that
exists is creeping us all out!
Get rid of it!
Take it all the way, huh?
A full exorcism?
Let me go over
our course pricing.
[STUDENT 03B] We'll take
the most expensive one.
You're goin' out there again?
That man keeps
wasting your time.
Still not mad, huh?
Whatever you can do,
please, just do it.
[gasps]
[MOB]
There are three of them.
But they don't seem
like bad spirits.
Well, the clients are scared,
and they're paying
for our services.
Get rid of 'em.
[DAD GHOST]
Please. Don't.
[DAD GHOST] Because the
three of us are a family...
We only had a few
short years together
before we died.
But now that we're spirits,
we can continue to exist
peacefully in this place.
We've done nothing wrong.
We just want to
spend a little more
time together as a family.
Once we've had that,
I promise you, we'll disappear.
So please... let us
remain in peace.
Master. Did you hear
anything he said?
[REIGEN]
Nope. Not a thing.
Their uh, aura was too weak.
Look, there's no need
to exorcise them.
They say they won't
do anything wrong.
And they're a family.
[STUDENT 03AA]
Hey! We hired you
for a specific
purpose! Remember?
It creeps me out just
knowing they're here!
It doesn't matter if they
do anything wrong or not!
We said we'd pay
for it, so do it!
[STUDENT 03AA]
Get rid of them already!
[STUDENT 03A] I don't even
wanna be out here, anymore!
[STUDENT 03AA]
I'm so freaked, I'm gonna hurl!
Come on. What's the hold up?
You've gotten rid of all kinds
of evil spirits before.
These aren't evil.
They only want
to exist in peace.
And I don't wanna take
that away from them.
It's not right.
Listen we don't care
how you feel about it.
We hired you for a job,
so just do it, okay!
Hey, mister!
We came to you
because we desperately
needed your help,
did you forget?
The client's needs
do take priority
in these situations.
[MOB gasps]
[REIGEN] But... If spirits
are every bit as worthy
of respect as the living...
And if all they're doing
is simply existing in
this place, peacefully...
...then barging in
and evicting them
by force like this is wrong.
I don't wanna make Mob
do something like that.
[REIGEN sighs]
But... these people
are really terrified here.
What am I supposed to do?
As a professional,
can I put ghosts
ahead of my clients?
Hey. Mister Ghost Listen.
You've got some power stored up
you've been keepin'
a secret, now don't you?
[MOB]
Dimple...
You've been savin' that power
as a way to try and protect
your family, right?
Then how about this?
Why not just kill these
idiots where they stand?
Think of it this way:
if the clients die,
then there'll be no reason
to get rid of you.
[DIMPLE]
You wanna stay here, don't ya?
Come on! It's the
only way ya can!
[gasps]
[MOM GHOST]
Honey...
[BOY GHOST]
Daddy...
[DAD GHOST]
Please. I beg you. Let us go.
I could never do
something so awful.
Not in front of my child.
[DIMPLE]
I see. Then what will you do?
[DAD GHOST]
We have nowhere to go,
so we're at your mercy.
If you want to cast us out,
we'll have to accept that.
But, if you do, at least...
...send us somewhere
we can be together...
...as a family.
[REIGEN] Mob. Are the spirits
still talking to you?
Mob, what are you--?
Yo. What's the holdup here?
Gimme a minute, all right?
Say something, Mob.
He doesn't wanna do this
so badly that he's shaking.
[REIGEN]
No kidding...
Okay, got it. We'll
leave them alone.
I'm not ordering you to
do anything, all right?
Everything is fine.
I trust your feelings on this.
Me, too.
Take it easy. You
can finally relax.
You've got a strong
heart, Shigeo.
[MOB] You don't
understand... I'm sure...
[gasps]
I'm sure that I'm the only
one who possibly could.
I mean, there's no way I can
act on my feelings alone.
I can't take this lightly.
If I decide I wanna
protect this family,
it might not stop there.
Who knows?
Protecting them could lead
to the clients getting hurt.
[gasps]
[STUDENT 03A]
Why is this taking so long?!
You're the boss! Just make him--
[STUDENTS yelp]
Ugh! What is this? Salt? Ugh!
[REIGEN]
There ya go. Exorcism's over.
[STUDENT 03A]
What?! Wait, seriously?
But I never saw
any ghosts, like--
It's over.
Uh, okay...
[REIGEN]
Tsk!
Reigen? So what's
gotten into you?
[REIGEN]
Ah, so that's it...
How did I not notice?
[REIGEN] He can do things
that other people can't.
The world he sees is
far greater than ours.
Curses, spirits...
They're all part
of his daily life.
Both humans and things
that aren't human
are equally close to him.
Damn it...
I took too many jobs, got lazy,
and half-assed things.
This is on me.
[REIGEN]
We're leaving.
Wanna get some soba?
[MOB]
Yeah.
[DIMPLE] You sure about
how you handled that?
You just threw fistfuls
of salt around everywhere,
said that was it,
and took their money.
What else was I supposed to do?
If I didn't take their money,
then they'd be suspicious.
Anyway, you confirmed they
weren't evil spirits, right?
Yeah. I tried to talk
them into turning evil,
but they weren't having it.
What's with the shaking?
[yawns]
[DIMPLE]
You're yawning?
Man, you're a piece of work.
Huh? Hey, it looks like there's
something on your back.
What?
[DIMPLE] Oh, yeah. Somebody
definitely cursed you.
What happens if I ignore it?
If you let it go
unchecked, who knows?
You might slip on a
banana peel or something.
That could prove fatal
if I was on the stairs.
Get rid of it.
No. Sorry, I don't think
I like your attitude.
Come on. I can't
ask Mob to do it.
That client from
yesterday probably
hired someone who could
really do the job.
Tsk! Fine, whatever.
[REIGEN] There are things
he may know about
that we can't see.
Really scary things
the rest of the world
may never come
face-to-face with.
[NARRATOR] Mob understood
that what he fears--
what he shirks from,
the trials and
tribulations he faces--
are different than those
of the rest of the world.
[MOB] If I wanted to use my
powers to curse someone...
Or use them to commit crimes
or wrongdoings of any kind...
If I ever thought I wanted
to get rid of a living,
breathing person,
and not just a spirit...
Would anybody be there...
...to stop me?
[NARRATOR]
Mob sat there and tried to think
about everything
that had happened
over the past two days...
But he may have
been too tired,
because he quickly
went to sleep.
[REIGEN] We were invited over
to a rich guy's mansion!
Oh, man, I smell a big job!
Let's make some money, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode four:
"Inside: Evil Spirit."
A video streaming service?
Obviously an excellent decision!