[OFFICE GUY 06A]
Ah, yes! Thanks, as always.
Of course!
And thank you for your
continued business!
[OFFICE LADY 06A]
Really?
Then we'll make
arrangements right away!
[OFFICE GUY 06B]
Oh, no. No, no, no, no!
Not at all! It's
all thanks to you!
Uh-huh!
Perfect. I'll take it.
Excellent decision, sir!
[REIGEN yawns]
[REIGEN]
I wonder what I should do now.
I rented this place without
having anything lined up.
[school bell rings]
[MOB]
...31... 32... 33...
...34...
Ugh...
Thirty...
[GODA]
Way to go! That's a new record!
You've gotten
stronger, Kageyama!
Time to celebrate!
[KUMAKAWA] Your muscles are
growing and evolving!
[SAGAWA] All that training
is finally paying off!
[DIMPLE] I thought his exercise
routine was a waste of time.
But, this goes way
beyond getting in shape.
All these improvements are
making him more confident.
Just look at that face.
He's glowing.
Looks like Mob's
having fun over there.
I've got an idea!
Why don't you grab him and
toss him in the air, too?
Today's his birthday, after all.
Huh? Uh, no thanks.
Kijibayashi. Is it
really your birthday?
Technically, yeah.
[yelps]
[GODA] There's just so much
to celebrate today!
Hey, President. It was
my birthday last week.
[GODA]
What?! How did we miss it?!
Then why don't we throw a
big group birthday party?
We could hit up a family
restaurant and have some fun!
I like the way
you think, Saruta!
[LADY 06A]
What is that?
An extremely rare
salt rock obtained
from the Uyuni Salt Flats,
just perfect for exorcisms!
[phone ringing]
Excuse me.
Hello? Spirits and
Such Consultations.
What? Frozen tofu spirits?
Of course, I've heard of them!
Leave everything to me.
[REIGEN]
It seems like I'm getting
one job after another lately.
[CLUB MEMBERS] ♪ Happy
birthday, happy birthday, ♪
♪ Kijibayashi and Kumakawa! ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
happy birthday, ♪
♪ happy birthday to you! ♪
[SHIMURA] We got the drink bar,
so feel free to have your fill!
You really surprised me, Mob.
I never thought you'd stick with
the Body Improvement
Club for so long.
[SARUTA] Yeah, I thought he'd
throw in the towel pretty quick.
Kageyama's persistent.
I'll give him that much.
So, do ya have some big
goal you wanna accomplish?
Hit it hard for
another six months,
and you could reach the level
of an average seventh grader.
Come on.
I'm sure 'ol Kageyama
has his sights set
on a much loftier
goal than that.
If we let our guards down,
he might pass us all up
before we know it!
He just wants to catch the
eye of the girl he likes.
[MOB gasps]
Well, it started out
that way, sure.
But now...
And by the way, Mob,
I hope that you
haven't forgotten.
You are supposed to help
me find other telepaths.
Oh. Still hoping
to meet some, then?
[TOME]
Of course, I am!
What do you think the point
of the Telepathy Club is?!
So anyway, about tonight.
[TOME]
I was talking!
Why don't we all go out
for a little karaoke?
Huh? Karaoke?
Yeah, dude. Have you
never been before?
All right! Let's do it!
It's not often we get
a chance like this!
Well, that is a good
point. If you insist.
[TOME]
What should I sing first?
Feeling self-conscious, Mob?
That all goes away,
once you start singing.
Maybe. I just don't
do this very often.
It's really nice.
Spending time hanging
out with friends...
[MOB]
It's so much fun!
[phone rings]
Hello, Master
[REIGEN]
What's shakin', Mob?
Hey, there's an evil spirit
giving me some trouble.
[REIGEN] I could totally
deal with it myself,
but there's been
so much work lately.
I'd rather not use
too much of my power--
Mob?
Master, could you handle
things on your own today?
[REIGEN]
Huh?
Uh...
We've talked about this.
I've asked you repeatedly
not to summon me
on such short notice.
[REIGEN]
What's this all about?
You're never busy!
What's the holdup?
Look, there's a client
here who could
really use your help.
I'll be waitin' for ya,
so try not to be too long.
Okay?
[dial tone]
What's the matter, Kageyama?
Is it that shady-ass
master of yours again?
A last-minute job came in,
so I won't be able
to go to karaoke.
I'm really sorry for missing
out on your birthdays.
Hey! It's fine.
Don't worry about us.
You've done plenty.
Glad you came.
People's jobs and
responsibilities take priority.
So we understand.
All those stories about
the ghost of a man
who hit his head on a block
of frozen tofu and died...
...they're actually true?
How about I make
you think of me...
...every time you
see a block of tofu?!
[CLIENTS scream]
Please! Get rid of him!
Have no fear.
I have my disciple
heading over immediately.
Nice one, Mob. Good job.
[REIGEN hums]
[REIGEN]
Hm?
What's wrong?
[MOB]
Despite what you think,
even I have school
and a private life.
So please, stop summoning
me out of the blue.
What do you mean,
"private life"?
All you have is that
exercise club, right?
[gasps]
[REIGEN] Wait, you didn't
fall for someone's
fake date prank again, did you?
Man, you are so gullible.
Would you grow up, already?
Seriously, Mob.
I don't know what
you were doing
with your little schoolmates,
but do they really
understand who you are?
Come on, you and I
are saving lives here!
You're making a huge
difference in this world
just by helping me out!
Not to mention, I'm your master!
I'm one of the biggest
reasons you're able
to control your powers!
Without me, you'd
be a lost cause!
Now, listen up.
Choose your social
circle wisely, Mob!
If anyone is going
to get in the way
of your exorcism job,
get rid of 'em!
Those kids don't actually
care about you at all.
Understand?
They're just having
fun mocking someone
as wimpy as you.
[MOB]
That's not true!
[REIGEN]
Huh?
Uh, all right, I might've
said too much there.
My friends aren't mocking me.
Yeah. Sure.
Master, I'm starting
to realize that
not everything you say is true.
[REIGEN]
Crap! I messed up!
Uh, let's forget all this,
Mob! You must be tired!
Hey. Wanna get some
ramen on the way back?
[MOB]
Nobody's mocking me.
And I'm not as
gullible as you think.
[REIGEN sighs]
Damn it, Mob...
I promised this client
we'd help in advance.
And this is when he
finally no-shows on me.
I guess I really did
open my big mouth
and say too much yesterday.
[REIGEN]
Still...
As far as I know,
he really doesn't have
anyone he can talk to about
his problems other than me.
If he cuts ties with me,
he'll end up alone again.
There's nothing to worry about.
He'll be back soon
enough. I know it.
Whoa, Brother.
You're home earlier than usual.
Oh, hey, Ritsu. Yeah, I...
I've decided not to go
to Master's place
for a little while.
Well, that's fine and all,
but what brought this on?
Reigen's mouth.
They had a fight and
Mob won't talk to him.
That has nothing to do with it.
I just thought
about it and decided.
For far too long, I've
been blindly following
what Master Reigen says.
I felt like things
went better that way.
So it was easier for me
just to go along with it.
But...
Would you grow up,
already? Seriously, Mob.
I can't just keep
relying on him forever.
So I figured I'd reconsider
what I wanna do a little more.
[RITSU]
Wanna play some video games?
[DIMPLE]
You messed up, Reigen.
And you got no one
to blame but yourself.
Oh, man!
I think I sweat off
whatever was haunting me.
I guess coral steam yoga
really was the best approach.
Glad to be of service.
[REIGEN] Thank goodness
it wasn't a real spirit.
[REIGEN]
Why am I so surprised, though?
I basically built this business
from the ground up
all by myself.
Why would it matter
if Mob's here or not?
I just need stay
focused and continue
taking on the types of jobs
I can do on my own.
Let the real psychics
deal with actual spirits.
Yeah! Now, not only can
I reduce labor costs,
I won't have to hear about his
teenage "dilemmas" anymore.
There's only so much
time in a day.
I should use it
to study and learn
more about the world.
Hey, I'm becoming pretty
optimistic about this.
Sorry, Mob. This probably wasn't
what you were expecting,
but I'm not upset
about this at all.
I'm sure you must be feelin'
pretty lonely right about now.
[REIGEN laughs]
[REIGEN]
I bet that, by now,
Mob is really regretting
his decision.
He probably feels awkward
about talking to me.
I'm a mature adult.
I understand. It's not like
I'd even care to begin with.
[REIGEN grunts]
No way!
It looks like he's
genuinely having fun!
Mob actually has friends?!
Why in the hell are
ya hiding, dumbass?
[yelps] Dimple!
What? I-I'm not hiding at all!
[DIMPLE] There's no need
to worry about Mob.
He's having fun.
Well, that's great
news, but he never
even crossed my mind!
It's really good to hear that.
Shigeo doesn't seem
to be concerned
about you or what you're
doing in the slightest.
It's been kinda peaceful.
[REIGEN]
What?!
Hmph!
And you're okay
with this, Dimple?
[DIMPLE]
What do ya mean?
The more he avoids me,
the less he'll have
the opportunity
to use his powers.
Do you really wanna
be an ordinary
middle schooler's pet forever?
Never being more than
what you are right now?
That would be kinda peaceful.
I always thought you wanted
to use Mob's powers
for yourself.
Sucks to be you.
Now that he's decided to lead
such an ordinary life,
he's of no use to anyone!
Oh, the humanity!
I hope ya have fun
following around
a regular ol' snot-nosed
middle schooler!
I, on the other hand,
will be taking my career
on up to the next level!
Yeah, sure.
Well, I'm glad to see that
you're doing all right.
If you can crack jokes
and be this happy,
there's no need to worry.
Who knows? We may never
see each other again.
Guess I'll use tonight
to update the homepage.
[MOB]
Huh? Aren't we going home?
We didn't find any telepaths,
so I figured we were
done for the day.
You couldn't sing with us before
'cause you had to work, right?
So now's your chance.
Let's do it!
[TOME] Think of it this way:
you'll be able to sense
a telepath if they're
nearby, right?
Then you can look and
sing at the same time.
Hold on! I'm not ready!
[TOME] Oh, relax.
Get in there. Live a little!
[REIGEN] A newbie idol's
blog got flamed, huh?
Hm.
Oh. Since I'm online,
I should check Friendbook.
It has been a while...
In this day and age,
you can connect
with the people
you know any time.
Talk about convenient.
Hey!
Looks like I have
a new message here!
Sorry for not reading it sooner.
I've just been
so busy, you know?
Who could it be?
Maybe it's the one
I met at the mixer.
Oh, yeah.
Right, I totally forgot.
Zero, huh?
[beeping]
Wait. Here we go.
[TOME, INUKAWA] ♪ So tell me,
do you like strange girls? ♪
♪ Melt, melt your brain with
a jolt of electronic waves. ♪
♪ Training to get a feel of
what it's really like. ♪
[INUKAWA]
Ya having a good time?
I think so?
[TOME, INUKAWA]
♪ Melancholy! ♪
Huh? You have no rhythm
at all, do you, Mob?
[INUKAWA]
Yeah! Wahoo!
Uh-uh.
Well, well, Reigen!
Welcome back. It's
been far too long.
It's Reigen!
Nice to see ya
here again, buddy!
What a surprise!
Come join us!
We need to catch up!
A lemon sour...
Go heavy on the sour.
Wait, should you be
drinking right now?
[REIGEN]
Yeah.
The regulars here are nice,
but they're also the type
of people who'd fall
for pyramid schemes,
fake cults, stuff like that.
And they all need that
certain someone to vent
their troubles to that can
help relieve their stress...
...and make them feel better...
[REIGEN] It's basically a gold
mine for someone like me.
A place where the
weak-minded gather.
Reigen, get a load of this one!
Just the other day,
this really pretty girl
started chattin' me up.
So I walked along with her
and she led me
to some art exhibit.
An exhibit where a copy
of a famous painting
was on display.
That's a dating scheme.
[REIGEN] I'll give them some
random words of advice.
In return, I get their respect.
They might be...
...the closest thing
I have to real friends.
[REIGEN]
So... it's my birthday today.
[ALL gasp]
Happy birthday.
Happiest of birthdays
to you, buddy.
Happy birthday.
Thanks. Cheers.
[BAR CUSTOMER 06B]
This is the perfect time
to bring this up since
it's your birthday!
I have this amazing pillow
I got through a
special connection.
It's super soft while
still being supportive!
It's made of this
unique memory foam!
You'll sleep like a baby!
It's worth 120,000 yen, but...
Reigen, that is your
first drink, right?
Your face is flushed.
You feeling okay?
Not the least bit.
[gasps] Hey, what's wrong?
Tab me out, please.
[REIGEN]
Well, that backfired.
I thought I wanted
to talk to someone.
To anyone.
It sure does suck to realize
you don't have any friends.
[BARKEEP] But I didn't even
put any alcohol in this.
[REIGEN grunting]
[REIGEN wretches]
[REIGEN]
This has gone south... fast.
I can't believe this
is happening to me.
Me, of all people!
Wait... Me?
I mean...
[REIGEN]
What--
What am I?
[REIGEN] I guess I'm
just gonna have to...
...become somebody.
[alarm beeps]
[NARRATOR] After ending up
alone and getting over it,
Reigen made huge
changes in his life.
You're in luck!
I, Reigen Arataka,
shall accept this job!
[NARRATOR] He started
using his time to help
beautify the city, he
live-streamed exorcisms online.
He held free seminars
and even offered
people life coaching
and counseling,
broadening his field of work.
But, he continued his usual
exorcism jobs with vigor.
One involved the
super-popular online game
Fantasy Hell .
There was a rumor that
the Player Killer
was actually a ghost.
It was a difficult job
that many other psychics
had declined to take.
Well, I've heard of it,
but I didn't even bother.
It's not something
we specialize in.
Our spiritual power can't
do anything inside a game.
Understand?
[NARRATOR]
Meaning it was a target even Mob
with all of his powers wouldn't
be able to exorcise.
However, Reigen used
multiple accounts
and stayed up late
night after night,
repeatedly leveling up and
strengthening his weapons.
He then baited the
ghost player out,
surrounded it, and beat
the living crap out of it.
In doing so, he finally
succeeded in the exorcism.
Y-You're amazing!
You actually exorcised
the Player Killer!
[CLIENT 06E]
How did you manage to do it?
As a psychic, it's
all in a day's work.
[REIGEN] I made too many
in-game purchases
and now I'm broke!
[NARRATOR]
Because of his success
at this well-publicized job,
the agency's notoriety
continued to grow.
[NARRATOR] Eventually,
someone started calling Reigen
"the Bro of Seasoning City"
and his popularity skyrocketed.
He was even interviewed
by a well-known magazine.
[NARRATOR]
Just a few days after that...
[REIGEN]
Wait... television?!
I'm so popular, you want
me to be on your show?
That's right!
One of our producers
happened to hear about you
and thought you'd be a
perfect fit for our program.
[REIGEN]
A national broadcast...
If you manage to get
popular on television,
you'll immediately shoot to
the top of the psychic world.
[EBIHARA] Today, on
Supernatural Detective ...
It's the "Do Spiritual Powers
Actually Exist?" special!
And we are comin' at you live!
I, Morizo Ebihara, am your host!
These are our guests:
sci-fi researcher
Tatsuya Moki and idol Satake!
--[MOGI] Thanks for having me.
--[SATAKE] Hello, everyone!
[EBIHARA] We also have
some psychics here with us
for this special program.
Thanks for joining us!
It's a pleasure to have ya!
Thanks. The pleasure's all mine.
[REIGEN]
Holy crap. I'm really on TV.
And everything's actually
going smoothly...
For today's show,
we've invited somebody
who claims to be possessed
by an evil spirit.
So, we'll have our
experts perform
an exorcism for you
right here, live on TV!
[REIGEN]
Are you for real?
Well, if I'm able to pull
this off like a rock star
on national TV, I'll
get even more fans.
All right.
[REIGEN, JODO]
I'm a little nervous,
but I'm gonna to show
them what I've got!
[JODO] ...is what you're
thinking, isn't it?
Your ego will deflate like
a sad balloon, you fool!
Who do you think mentioned you
to the program's producers?
It was I, Jodo!
My disciples told me all about
what happened that day!
About how you had
the nerve to nail me
with a jumping knee strike!
You're going to pay
dearly for that!
I'll make damn sure you
regret it for the rest
of your pathetic life!
[REIGEN] The new star
of the 21st century,
Reigen Arataka,
makes his TV debut
on a national program!
Hmph! Look at me!
Watch me shine, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho
100 II , episode seven:
"Cornered ~True Identity~."
The Blu-rays? That's an
even better decision.