What would drive you
to become a serial killer,
Superintendent Kagami?
[KAGAMI]
Don't call me that.
I'm not a
superintendent anymore.
[KAGAMI] I'm starting to think
it was destined to end this way.
The moment that someone like me
became a member of
law enforcement.
Congratulations!
[KAGAMI] We lost our parents
while I was still in college.
I had started working part-time
so my kid sister
Tokiko could move in.
But we needed something steady.
We were so close back then.
My brother, with a career
in law enforcement!
With a state job like this,
you're set for life!
Yeah.
We shouldn't have to worry
about money anymore.
And I'll be able to support
your fashion career.
[TOKIKO]
Kagami!
Don't make me your charity
case, I'll be fine.
And while you're at it,
enough about budgets!
You should celebrate!
--Here!
--[KAGAMI] Huh?
A gift, for the start
of your career, Silly.
Wear it with pride!
It's perfect.
[TOKIKO giggles]
[KAGAMI] Keisuke Kagami,
First Investigation Division,
reporting for duty!
Nice to meet you, sir!
[NAKAMURA laughs] You know,
you don't have to be so formal!
Your desk's right there.
[DETECTIVE A]
Chief, there's been a murder!
[DETECTIVE B]
Got it. Where at?
[DETECTIVE A]
Ward Office Street Intersection.
--[DETECTIVE B] I'll drive!
--A murder? Already?
[NAKAMURA] Yeah, you got some
bad luck, if you're running
into a homicide your
first day, Little Kagami.
Wait, what? Little?
You're not talkin'
to me, are ya?
Uh, yeah? Who else would I mean?
[KAGAMI]
Hey! I don't like that!
C'mon, Little Kagami.
[KAGAMI] That first day,
I made a solemn vow.
Not just to the force,
but to myself.
To do everything I could
to protect the innocent.
[door rattles]
[TOKIKO]
Oh, I didn't know you were back.
[KAGAMI]
I didn't know you were still up.
I've been working on my
portfolio for that competition.
Kagami... You've been
coming home late every day.
Do the police really demand
that much from a rookie cop?
Yeah. That's just how it is.
[TOKIKO] Well, don't
push yourself too hard.
[KAGAMI]
Look, Tokiko.
Sad things happen
every day in this world.
And when you're a detective,
it's impossible to ignore them.
So I view it as my job
to make things less sad.
[TOKIKO]
But I know how you can get.
You can't help everyone, Kagami.
You'll burn out.
And then I'll be
the one who's sad.
You worry too much,
you know that?
Excuse me for caring about
the only family I have left.
Now, show you care
by going to bed!
Yeah, okay. Whatever.
But hey, you don't
push too hard, either.
[TOKIKO]
I won't.
[KAGAMI panting]
You're under arrest for
rape and manslaughter!
[NAKAMURA]
Nice job out there!
Yes, thank you, sir.
Couldn't have done it without
your help, Mister Nakamura.
This was your first
arrest, wasn't it?
Well... Guess I can't
call ya "little" now.
Right, Kagami?
[gasps]
That's right!
Thank you for that, sir.
--[phone vibrates]
--Sorry 'bout this.
[NAKAMURA] Hm? Is that your
girlfriend or somethin'? Huh?
I'm still at work.
Can this wait?
Hm? Oh... Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, no problem.
My kid sister.
She's making dinner tonight,
so she wants me sitting at
the table by six o'clock sharp.
She really needs a boyfriend.
Well, that's interesting.
All this time I thought you
might be running around
with some guy's wife, but
it's just your younger sister.
What?
[NAKAMURA] I'll be sure to
tell the girls in the office
that not only aren't you dating
anyone, you've got a big heart.
You're the most eligible
bachelor on the force.
Hey! Nakamura, c'mon!
[KAGAMI] Violent crimes
happened all the time.
The workload grew and grew.
But I never got angry.
If anything, I felt a
great sense of purpose.
I wanted to protect
the innocent.
But then came the day, where
I felt that purpose waver.
Acquitted?!
Yeah, the guy you nabbed
for those street attacks
won't set foot inside a cell.
And he wasn't acquitted, they
dropped the charges altogether.
Not that it really
matters in the end.
[KAGAMI]
What? Why would they do that?!
"Due to pathological
intoxication
caused by heavy drinking,
means the accused could be
considered temporarily
insane during his attacks,
and thus, not
legally responsible."
Basically, the State
can't charge this guy
because he was drunk
when he did it.
The insanity defense?!
That's like something
out of a bad TV show.
It's not gonna work
in a real trial!
[NAKAMURA]
Yeah, if it even goes to trial.
See, if an initial
psych eval on a perp
comes back with any
possibility of insanity,
they don't even
bother to prosecute.
Huh.
[NAKAMURA] Because an
insane defendant means
there's a damn good chance
the state loses at trial.
And trial losses hurt
a prosecutor's
chances at promotion.
Look. No matter what,
they're still gonna send the
guy to a psychiatric hospital.
[KAGAMI] On average, suspects
committed to psych hospitals
end up back on the streets
in just a few months.
Which is exactly what happened
with that first man I arrested.
And sure enough,
he killed again.
This latest murder was committed
by a man the police released
after dropping a previous
set of murder charges.
It's quite unfortunate.
And I'm afraid, fairly common.
Under the current penal
code, criminals found to be
legally incompetent due to
insanity cannot be punished.
[NEWSCASTER 4A]
So we're supposed to accept
insane murderers
walking the streets?
[SCHOLAR] No, no. After the
state drops criminal charges...
[TOKIKO]
What's with the gloomy face?
[KAGAMI gasps]
Oh, sorry.
Just thinking about something
that happened at work today.
Please don't tell me
the veteran officers
have been picking on you.
You're so serious,
and I know how those guys
love busting chops.
So if they are, let me know
and I'll go file a
citizen's complaint.
[KAGAMI]
No, that's not it at all!
[sighs]
I'm finding a lot of
evil goes unpunished.
I guess you could say I'm kind
of having a crisis of faith.
You'll get through this.
Because you're the
hardest working,
most honest man on
the police force!
Tokiko...
[TOKIKO] But compared to
everything you do, I'm nothing.
Nobody likes my designs.
My last one didn't get
a single good review.
[KAGAMI]
It wasn't fair.
I knew better than anyone--
especially critics--
how hard my sister worked
and how talented she was.
She worked hard every day
on her college assignments,
never doing anything
with friends.
And then she'd spend what little
free time she had at night
working on her designs.
Someone will recognize
your talent soon.
I'm sure of it.
You're the best.
Thank you.
There're so many.
What are you looking at there?
Mister Nakamura.
[NAKAMURA]
Coffee?
Thanks, I could use it.
I was looking through
all the cases
where the State
declined to indict.
There are way more
than I thought.
Yeah, I think last year
for murder cases,
it was a little less than half.
Hard to believe one out of
every two murderers we catch
ends up back on the streets.
Then what's the point?!
Why are we even bothering to
catch them in the first place?!
This isn't justice.
Yeah, sure is a cluster.
[NAKAMURA]
You ever hear of "Twenty Faces"?
[KAGAMI gasps]
Yeah. I mean, how could I not?
He was all over the
news last year.
A serial killer who only
kills other criminals.
Seems like he's bothered
by the same problem
that you've discovered.
Though, I'm no fan of
his solution to it.
It's arrogant for a man to think
he alone can identify
and punish evil.
Be careful how you
define "justice."
[KAGAMI] Not long after that
night, I first met... him.
You Keisuke Kagami?
Akechi. Detective.
Imperial Agency?
[AKECHI]
From here on out,
loop me in on any new evidence
you turn up on Twenty Faces.
Or on those you think
are just copycats.
Sure, but that's a
pretty big request.
I mean, I get what your
badge entitles you to.
I'm still a rookie, though.
If anything, you should
ask my supervisor--
I looked at the profiles of
every detective
in this precinct.
You seemed like the most
honest and trustworthy.
But... Men like you
tend to corrupt easily.
Don't let the darkness take you.
[KAGAMI]
Twenty Faces' vigilantism
spoke to my raw emotions,
but I wasn't so easily seduced.
I still believed
in the rule of law.
So I listened to reason
and tried to stay on
the straight and narrow.
I focused on the
righteousness of my work.
The traditional idea of justice.
And it served me well.
I got promoted to
superintendent.
[NAKAMURA] I guess
I gotta be more respectful
in how I address you now.
[KAGAMI gasps]
Oh, come on.
You really don't have
to change anything.
My dad always said
any organization
that doesn't have clearly
defined hierarchies
won't succeed in the long run.
It's important that you
own your higher position.
Superintendent Kagami.
You're right.
[KAGAMI] But throwing myself
into a police career like that,
meant that I was ignoring
my deep-seated doubts,
instead of confronting them
head-on like I should have.
[KAGAMI]
Huh?
[TOKIKO snoring]
[KAGAMI sighs]
Hey, Tokiko.
You'll hurt your back sleeping
on the couch like that.
[TOKIKO]
Next time...
They'll definitely...
like them next time.
[KAGAMI gasps]
Yeah.
You're working too hard.
You'll make it big someday.
I'm positive.
[KAGAMI]
But there are just...
...too many criminals who
don't have human hearts.
And the fact hardened my own.
It's over!
Man... I'm outta shape.
[KAGAMI] You're under
arrest, you monster!
[SUNAGA laughs]
Hey...
I've been in and outta plenty
of psychiatric hospitals before.
I bet ya.
I get acquitted due
to reasons of insanity
if it ever goes to trial.
One thing me and the
government have in common
is we don't put much
value on people's lives!
Sunaga!
Don't do it!
You'll be no better than him.
[KAGAMI]
Sorry...
[SUNAGA laughing]
[WATANUKI]
Haven't you learned
that it's foolish for you
to keep arresting me?
What?
As long as the eggheads
say I'm mentally ill,
I won't be competent
enough to stand trial.
That's why you keep dropping
the charges and releasing me.
Don't underestimate justice.
It won't let you get away
with your crimes forever!
Yeah, but even if
I was convicted,
they'd give me a light sentence
due to what they call,
"reduced mental capacity."
And since I'm rich,
once I'm free,
I could still live with a--
Why'd you hit me?!
You're a freak.
--[WATANUKI] You can't hit me!
--[NAKAMURA] Superintendent, no!
[WATANUKI] I'm gonna sue!
I have a mental illness!
I'm a protected
class of citizen!
[NAKAMURA]
Are you feeling less crazy now?
I'm so sorry.
I got too emotional.
[sighs]
It's bad timing, but you
should hear it from me.
They declined to indict that
frog-faced creep, Sunaga.
They're recommending
he be committed
to a psychiatric hospital.
[KAGAMI]
I see.
[NAKAMURA] Look, don't let
any of this discourage you.
This sorta case--
releasing perps--
you've seen a lot of 'em, right?
Helluva lot more
than me, I assume.
I just-- How have you
kept from losing it?
Well, I developed my own
take on how things work.
Even if they don't get indicted,
let alone convicted,
the time we do have
them under arrest
keeps them from
committing some crime,
at least for a little while.
I don't look it now, but when
I first started this gig,
I was by far the most passionate
detective in the precinct.
I can't.
Rationalizing things like
that, it's not who I am.
Yeah, you're stubborn.
[KAGAMI]
Sunaga walking changed me.
I had pushed down the
darkness, deep into my soul.
But now I started
seeing it again.
--[door rattles]
--[KAGAMI gasps]
Oh, Kagami!
I didn't know you were home.
Sorry. Just got back.
Why don't you turn
on some lights?
You hungry?
You want some dinner?
Yeah, that'd be great.
'Kay. I'll whip something up.
It won't be fancy, though!
[TOKIKO]
So, does it taste good?
[KAGAMI]
It's perfect.
[TOKIKO chuckles]
Before you joined the police,
we ate dinner every night
and now I barely
remember your face.
I feel so lonely.
[KAGAMI]
Tokiko, you sound like a child.
[TOKIKO growls]
You're comparing me to a child
when you can't even
make your own dinner?
Hold on!
I almost forget to tell you!
[KAGAMI]
What?
[TOKIKO chuckles]
You ready?
That blue dress pattern I
came up with a while back.
I got second place at
the design competition!
Tokiko, that's awesome!
[TOKIKO] My teachers and
classmates were totally shocked.
I mean, in a good way.
That's great to hear.
I'm so proud of you.
[KAGAMI]
Well, that settles that.
Tomorrow, I am definitely
coming home early to celebrate.
I'll pick up a cake, too.
That's the first time I've seen
a real smile on your
face in months.
[YOUNG MAN 4A]
Hm... Sorry, Pal.
I don't remember.
No problem.
Thank you.
[sighs]
So much for getting home early.
[phone rings]
Yeah, what's goin' on?
[NAKAMURA] Sorry to bug you,
but it's urgent.
What, did something happen?
[NAKAMURA] Sunaga escaped
from the psych hospital.
[KAGAMI]
What?!
[NAKAMURA] He killed a
nurse on his way out.
[KAGAMI gasps]
[NAKAMURA] And he sent us a
threatening email that says,
"As revenge for my arrest
at the hands of
Superintendent Keisuke Kagami,
I'm going to kill his family."
Are you with your
sister right now?
No. I was finishing
up on another case.
Far as I know, she's at home.
I'm on my way there right now.
[NAKAMURA] You need to get
to her as quickly as possible!
Yeah... Yeah!
[phone dialing]
Pick up, Tokiko!
Tokiko!
Pick up!
[NAKAMURA]
We found her.
Your sister's body was
severely mutilated.
Kagami...
I'm so sorry.
[KAGAMI crying]
[yells]
[sobs]
[KAGAMI]
What was I thinking being a cop?
It's all been a waste
of time and life!
The law can't protect anyone!
[KAGAMI]
We can't deter crime
with bureaucrats
waving around badges.
We need something stronger.
Something far, far stronger.
I knew it was only a matter
of time until you caught me.
So I did what I could.
Punished as many as possible,
even if it meant I got sloppy.
And just like when
I was an honest cop,
I worked day and night at it.
I couldn't help but notice
that Sunaga wasn't among
the bodies we found.
Does that mean you
didn't kill him?
No.
He's still alive.
I'd never just kill him.
[KAGAMI] I started by
gouging out his eyes.
Then, I cut off his limbs.
They're melting in
a tub at my home,
while what's left of
him soaks in chemicals
that slowly eat him alive.
I want him to look exactly
like Tokiko did when she died.
[KAGAMI] And that's...
almost the end of my tragedy.
All that's left is for you
to condemn me to death.
You can't let criminals go.
You must punish them.
[NAKAMURA sighs]
[NAKAMURA]
We're done here.
[POLICE]
Sir.
I die.
But Twenty Faces lives on.
How could you do these things?
Why couldn't you stay the Little
Kagami I met on your first day?
Kagami...
Well, time to rebuild
my little girl collec--
[thud]
[WATANUKI groans]
[SACHIKO'S FATHER]
You took my daughter from me.
You killed... my Sachiko!
This is judgement.
This is your judgement!