[NAKAMURA sighs]
Can't believe the accomplice
was one of our own.
We didn't even see it coming.
I'm guessing that you're pretty
proud of yourself, aren't ya?
[giggles]
[NAKAMURA] Don't try to
be cute. So, let's talk.
Do you have any idea
where Twenty Faces went?
Did he happen to let you in
on what he's planning next?
[MINAMI]
It's a metamorphosis.
Awareness is beginning to emerge
within social consciousness.
People aren't bound
by the same rules.
They're flying freely now.
My little brother's
death has served
a greater purpose, as will mine.
[MINAMI cackles]
[MINAMI]
And it's almost time.
[REPORTER 11A]
Wait a second.
I think someone is stepping
out onto the tower now.
Reporting from the scene.
First revealed by an anonymous
letter delivered to our station.
Someone who appears to be
Twenty Faces has shown up.
[NAMIKOSHI] Look. It's a
perfect night to die.
[clock tower chimes]
[REPORTER 11A] Well, it's
11 o'clock on the dot.
What do you think
he's going to do?
Though his intentions
are unknown,
if you look, you can
clearly see the young man
who committed self-immolation
at Shinjuku Station
three years ago.
What we have here
is a master vigilante
who has made a big reveal
in order to glorify himself
--to the public.
--Um, what about reports that
his appearance has already
started inspiring riots?
[NEWSCASTER 2A] Clearly,
he has tapped into a current
of deep dissatisfaction
running through society.
Perhaps it's his goal to
bring it to the surface.
[NAMIKOSHI]
Now. Let's start a revolution.
[REPORTER 11A gasps]
They're standing on the edge!
Are they going to jump?
[NAMIKOSHI]
The child you see here
has been victimized
for most of his life.
It's tragic.
The people who were
supposed to protect him
completely ignored any cries
for help. They let him suffer.
His parents had a
reputation to uphold.
[STUDENT 11A]
Seriously?
[STUDENT 11B]
No way!
Do we have any knowledge about
what the perpetrator's
intentions could be?
What is he planning
to do with the hostages?
Those kids gathered
here voluntarily
to be a part of this.
[REPORTER 11A gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Clearly.
The series of Twenty Faces
attacks have inspired them.
They decided, of their
own free will,
to become sacrifices
for his cause.
[NAMIKOSHI]
This girl is...
[BLACK LIZARD] It's impressive
that he's been able
to gather so many
people together.
Damn! I can't get ahold
of Kobayashi! Why?
[BLACK LIZARD] Your little
boyfriend must have been
sucked into this Twenty Faces
phenomenon as well.
He'll probably be taking
part in the suicide show
with the rest of them.
[grunts]
[BLACK LIZARD] The intention
is to convince people
to rise up against
their oppressors.
But dying won't help anything!
[BLACK LIZARD]
The weak tend to go for the most
extreme course of action.
I wonder if the
poor little things
are trying to give meaning
to their lives by dying.
How foolish.
[NAMIKOSHI] They'll jump off
the building, one by one,
every five minutes.
Private Detective Akechi.
Can you be the savior
for these damaged souls?
You're more than
welcome to stop by
for a nice visit, alone.
Now, does anyone have any
idea who this "Akechi" is?
No police or riot squadrons
are allowed in our vicinity.
Or we'll all jump together.
Pull back some! We need
to do whatever he says!
I wonder. How many
people can be saved?
[AKECHI sighs]
[BLACK LIZARD] He's clearly
provoking you to action.
What do we do now?
I'll stop this.
If he wants me to go alone,
then that's what I'll do.
You must remember that he's
planned ahead by working
all of your actions
into the calculations as well.
You need to think everything out
before you try and
play the hero, dear.
Though it's really sexy.
His formula can't
predict my actions.
How sweet!
I find it so adorable that
an experienced detective
like you can still be
undeterred by reality!
Ah... All right!
Convince them to let me
out and I'll help you.
I don't need your help.
You're completely
worthless to me.
[whimpers]
Ah! Yes! You know
what I like, Akechi!
I give up. Do whatever
you want with me!
If you come back alive,
I'll be here waiting for you
to make me your slave!
Teach this filthy girl a lesson!
Ravage me day and night!
[REPORTER 11C]
Hey, it's him!
[REPORTER 11D]
It's Akechi!
[REPORTER 11E]
He's coming out! There he is!
Hey! Who's in charge
of handling the media?
We need room to get by! Hello?
[REPORTER 11C]
Sir! Any words?
[REPORTER 11D]
Step aside! Speak up!
[REPORTER 11E]
What exactly is your involvement
with Twenty Faces?
[NAKAMURA]
Give the kid room!
Move! Outta the way!
Help! Akechi!
If you don't
hurry up and go now,
those children are
as good as dead!
That's right, so move it!
[REPORTER 11E]
Just give us one quick interview
since you're already here!
What a delight it
would be if life...
...was more than the
temporary madness
we're forced to endure.
I welcome death.
I imagine it to be
the sweetest release.
--A tender kiss goodbye
--[AKECHI] Move!
[NAMIKOSHI] at the helm of
social reconstruction.
[AKECHI]
Get out of my way!
[REPORTER 11A]
Someone jumped!
A boy just jumped
off the building!
--[thud]
--[CROWD screams]
Twenty Faces is trying
to tell all of us...
...that we need
to make a change!
[MAN 11A]
No one gives a hand to the weak!
[WOMAN 11A]
We get bullied more than anyone!
[WOMAN 11B]
Bad guys aren't punished!
[MAN 11B]
Rules and laws don't function!
[WOMAN 11C]
This society is so messed up!
--[WOMAN 11D] Raise your voice!
--[MAN 11C] Just wake up!
[AKECHI]
Dammit! Move!
[grunts]
[HASHIBA]
Akechi!
[NAKAMURA]
All right, who did that?
[AKECHI grunts]
[AKECHI] They must be
Namikoshi's sympathizers.
[AKECHI] The city is
probably full of them.
I'll have to go through them
to make it to the tower.
This isn't gonna be easy.
[AKECHI grunts]
[REPORTER 11B gasps]
Another person just jumped!
I was the first in a
long line of Twenty Faces.
And now...
I truly believe that
society's awakening
will continue after
I have passed on.
It really makes no difference
who is wearing the mask.
They are protected by
their brothers and sisters,
the souls of the anguished
seek true comfort...
...by transforming the
world that scarred them.
He's manipulating
your deepest fears!
Why can't you get that?
[AKECHI]
Hey. It seems you're confused.
I'm the man you want.
And I challenge you to fight me.
One at a time though.
Not all of you at once.
Help me!
[SHADOW MAN sighs] It's a good
thing those guys are idiots.
[AKECHI] It's about time
you showed up to help.
[SHADOW MAN] Oh, so you
knew that I was going
to be coming to your
rescue? How'd you know?
[AKECHI]
Hmph.
You're the Gentleman Thief.
[SHADOW MAN]
Go save those children.
Akechi.
I'll keep these guys distracted
while you make a break for it.
You and I have some
unfinished business.
So... don't die tonight.
Yeah. Same to you.
They're closing in.
I'll buy time for as long as
I can. I hope you make it.
All right, this is it.
What are you gonna do, Akechi?
[tires screech]
[grunts]
Akechi! Let's get going!
Hashiba!
[screeching]
[SHADOW MAN]
I outsmarted them all!
Well. It's all in their hands.
Can you shed light on the
shadows of this world, Akechi?
I didn't know you had a bike.
We had to leave,
so I borrowed it.
I broke the law because
I didn't have a choice.
No! The light's turning red!
[AKECHI]
Just speed up!
[HASHIBA yelps]
[NAKAMURA]
Four have already jumped?!
There should have already
been a rescue team
at the clock tower!
Why's it taking so long
to get anything done?
[VOICE 11A] The radio signals
are getting crossed!
There's too much
happening at once!
[NAKAMURA]
Dammit!
Hey! I'm Detective Akechi!
Will you let me through here?
What now?
[AKECHI]
Everyone's in my way today.
This can't be happening.
Twenty Faces wants him to come!
Why are you interfering?
Resistance. This is
all part of his plan.
[MACHO MEN grunt]
[gasps]
What the hell? Why are you here?
You're the boyfriend
of our mistress.
Which means we treat
you as our master.
I'm not her boyfriend.
And don't call me master.
[MACHO MAN 4A]
We defend!
Or else the mistress
will have our asses
when we get back.
[TWENTY FACES 11V groans]
[MACHO MAN A grunting]
[TWENTY FACES 11W groans]
Enlighten me, just why are
all of your friends psychotic?
Lucky, I guess.
Right behind you!
[helicopter blades whirring]
I think we're coming in
a little too close!
We were ordered to stand by.
[PILOT 11A]
I think we need to cover this.
[REPORTER 11A]
We do?
Do you know something
that the station doesn't?
[PILOT 11A]
Not really.
There are important
things happening tonight,
and I'm letting the need
for change drive my actions.
Don't worry.
You aren't in danger.
[gasps] Can... I
continue reporting?
[PILOT 11A]
I'd actually prefer if you did.
The world needs to know
exactly what's going on here.
So, it appears that
a man we can only
assume to be Detective Akechi
has entered the clock tower.
At this time, a total
of five boys and girls
have jumped to their deaths.
We can only hope that
he can put an end
to this horrific situation.
Kobayashi is here.
We can save him!
I'll take care of that.
You just try to stay alive.
What about Namikoshi?
[AKECHI]
I can only save one.
[HASHIBA gasps]
[AKECHI] If Kobayashi dies,
the guilt will haunt me.
If Namikoshi dies, his law
will be fully operational,
and society will crumble.
Can you really
see yourself letting
your best friend die?
[AKECHI] I understand
your issue with that,
but you can't be so naive.
Friendship has limits.
No it doesn't!
I won't let him die!
[gasps]
In the end, we may not've
found satisfaction,
but we did manage
to get some revenge.
Even if we did go
about it the wrong way,
it was better than sitting
back being a victim.
Everybody has the right
to defend themselves.
Through your selfless efforts,
they'll see that they
no longer have to
suffer in silence.
That makes me glad.
That might just get me into
Heaven with my brother.
Miss Minami is
probably gone by now.
She was fun.
I really liked the way
she explained the murders.
[NAMIKOSHI]
Though they have to die,
martyrs have significance.
Dark Star will
leave a deep wound,
but it will pave the way
for a new world to be born.
So everyone is going to suffer?
[NAMIKOSHI]
Yes. Then they'll understand.
I find you
interesting, Namikoshi.
I feel the same.
Aren't you frightened?
Yeah, maybe a little bit,
but I'm having a lot of fun.
[NAMIKOSHI]
I see.
You really are the type who'd
want to be Akechi's assistant.
[REPORTER 11A]
There's another one!
A sixth person has jumped!
Somebody tell me
why the live footage
is still air--
[REPORTER 11B]
Large crowds influenced
by the clock tower suicides
are beginning to riot.
Citizens have gone
into mass hysteria!
[SYMPATHIZERS]
Judgment! Judgment! Judgement!
Judgement! Judgment!
Judgment! Judgement!
Judgement! Judgment! Judgment!
Judgement! Judgement!
[grunts]
Namikoshi.
Akechi.
That's amazing!
He arrived here right when
you said he was going to!
Kobayashi, stop letting
him poison your mind.
Come here.
Huh...
[AKECHI]
Right now!
But the world could
be a better place.
Namikoshi's methods
may be violent,
but what if they can
spark lasting change?
Sometimes, that's the only way.
If revolution is a possibility,
then the losses
might be worth it.
And besides,
I never really felt like
I've belonged in this world,
so I think I should take this
opportunity to use my life
for something
greater than myself.
Wake up!
[NAMIKOSHI] I can certainly
sympathize with him.
Most people walk
through life in a daze,
while only a few are awake.
Don't you agree?
Hello, Akechi. Are you
happy to see me?
I know how effective the
formula can be on society.
Of course you do.
However, if the creator
has to die in the end,
the formula is defective.
Death is a necessary
element for this rebirth.
All of the pieces
are falling together.
[NAMIKOSHI] In the end, it
doesn't matter which one of us
dies tonight. The remorse
will be devastating,
and eventually, you, too, will
become a catalyst for change.
I'm really sorry that's going
to happen to you, Akechi.
[AKECHI]
Shut up.
Ever since I was little,
I found life to be so boring.
But since I've been
investigating things with you,
it's been wonderful!
I said, shut up!
[gasps]
Since you met my challenge...
As I promised. They'll stop
dying for this great cause.
Though we... must
fulfill our roles.
But, why?
Kobayashi, will you join me?
[KOBAYASHI]
Yes.
Wait!
[AKECHI]
Don't do it!
[gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
This is for the best.
They can finally reconcile.
[KOBAYASHI]
Yep.
Considering this was my idea,
I think it turned out
to be a good one in the end.
Hashiba!
[HASHIBA yells]
[gasps]
[HASHIBA grunts]
You saved me.
Trying to die?
Why would you do
something so stupid?
Hashiba. Why would you jump?
You could have died saving me.
My best friend was about
to fall to his death!
What else was I s'posed to do?
I'm not going to let you die!
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
[HASHIBA sobs]
Stop being selfish!
You never consider
anyone else's feelings!
Don't you know how
much you mean to me?
[HASHIBA sobs]
I do.
[gasps]
[AKECHI]
So...
We managed to alter
the expected results.
I'll keep reworking it,
as many times as it takes.
A-Akechi...
[AKECHI]
I finally saved you.
I'm glad you did.
[clock tower chimes]
[NAMIKOSHI]
But...
If I live tonight, there's no
way to prove our omniscient law.
[gasps] No! Please don't!
[NAMIKOSHI]
I must.
I have to... show you
its perfection. We did it.
[AKECHI]
No!
[NAMIKOSHI]
Finally, the Dark Star we shared
will be able to gleam. Goodbye.
Thank you... Akechi.
I swear, I'm really okay.
[HASHIBA] You'll be swarmed by
reporters if you don't get in.
I guess you're right.
I'll visit you
later then, Hashiba.
U-Uh! Yeah.
[NAKAMURA]
Hey! Over here.
Hm?
[HASHIBA]
Do you think it's over?
Question.
What is it?
Tell me.
Why did you risk your
life for him back there?
The truth is: I'm heir to
the Hashiba Foundation.
Back in elementary school,
I didn't exactly fit in with
everyone else in the class.
But then, Kobayashi came
into my life one day.
He was nice to me.
Thought of me as more
than just a rich kid.
Before I knew it,
we'd become friends.
There were those
who called me names,
but Kobayashi would
always stand up for me.
I've never told him,
but I was so grateful.
I learned what friendship means.
It's being there to love
someone despite inconvenience.
You think so?
Yeah.
The city's been calm, hasn't it?
[meows]
It's only been six months.
Hard to believe that so
much corruption occurred
and no one is talking about it.
Society has more complexities
than you kids could
ever hope to imagine.
It's dumbfounding.
You realize that you're
a kid, too, right?
[AKECHI]
Not with the things I've seen.
[gasps] They never found
Namikoshi's body?
That's interesting.
[AKECHI] His sympathizers
probably took it, maybe.
I actually hope he's alive.
You think the world is
spinning just to make
our dreams come true?
Now you're implying
that wishful thinking
is a bad thing?
[AKECHI]
Maybe.
[HASHIBA]
Geez.
Ah.
I can sleep.
[KOBAYASHI] There isn't
much hope in this world.
I can see that now. I used to
think I didn't really care
if I went on living.
But that's changed.
I feel like things are
getting kinda fun.
[meows]
[phone rings]
[footsteps]
If that's a new case,
we'll take it!