[KOBAYASHI] Our homeroom
teacher has been murdered.
To make things worse, the
investigation also revealed
that he was a
serial killer himself,
and that he committed
his bizarre crimes
in his dead parents' garage.
Due to the circumstance
in which he was found
and some other evidence,
I'm suspected of being
not only his accomplice,
but his murderer, too.
You'd think I'd be worried.
But this is the most
fun I've ever had!
Kobayashi!
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
[HASHIBA gasps]
Please try.
It's okay. I didn't
do it, Hashiba.
[NEWSCASTER 2A]
A junior high school student
was arrested last night
on charges of mass murder
in a Shinjuku
multi-tenant building.
This same student is
also the key witness
in a recent teacher murder case,
which you saw here first.
So the question seems to be:
What drives a young
boy to violence?
The problem lies
with the system,
which refuses to address
these kids' issues!
Well, to put it simply, these
young people have "game brain."
They've been completely
desensitized.
Our children are
precious treasures.
They need our love,
not our constant judgment.
Now in other
legislative news,
an increase in sales tax is
likely to pass in the Diet.
I mean, I was like, "Man,
the tax is gonna go way up,
even though my salary's gonna--"
[STUDENT A] I think that kid
they keep talking about on TV
is actually Kobayashi!
[STUDENT B]
Are you serious?
So they said he was
actually arrested, then?
[STUDENT C]
Hey, Hashiba?
Is Kobayashi really
out sick again today?
Yeah, he's still at home.
But he's the suspect
from the news, isn't he?
'Course not.
He's just not feeling
well, that's all.
Oh...
But how can you be
sure that Kobayashi
--wasn't involved in the--
--[HANABISHI] Good morning,
sweet class! [giggles]
Okay! Please take
your seats, everyone!
Oh my goodness.
What's this cell
phone doing here?
Let's see.
Kids, did one of you
lose your phone?
[HASHIBA]
Ms. Hanabishi.
I think that cell might've
belonged to our
previous teacher.
I heard the police say
they weren't able to find
it during their search.
Oh my! That's exciting!
Well, in that case,
I'll be sure to
take it by the police
station after school.
[KAGAMI]
As you know, Kobayashi,
we've discovered multiple bodies
at your teacher's
parents' house.
That's why you're here.
We also found the
murder weapons.
And you just randomly
found them there?
No, we were tipped off. And
at the informant's insistence,
we checked out the garage.
[KOBAYASHI]
Could you move your hand?
No, sir.
You're thirteen, you
don't need to see it.
But I've already seen
the human chairs.
[KAGAMI sighs]
[KAGAMI] The bodies, it seems,
have been perfectly preserved.
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
I'm impressed.
You can take quite a bit, huh?
The anonymous tip.
Akechi said the killer
would want attention.
Hey.
You're a star, kid.
But that was never
my intention,
I thought you were going
to impose media control.
No point now.
The killer leaked the
info on the internet.
That means it'll be general
knowledge in no time.
All the teacher's murders.
[KOBAYASHI]
The killer's goal is to
make everyone think the
teacher deserved to die.
They want the public
to hate him, right?
But it didn't happen at first
because we didn't let it happen.
The killer began to
lose their patience.
And now, they want revenge
on the teacher so badly, they
decided they couldn't wait.
They took the risk.
So that means you
used me as bait!
[AKECHI] Well, you're a
suspect too, remember?
[gasps] I keep forgetting.
Aren't we lucky. Such a
shrewd young detective.
[KAGAMI] Your prints were
all over the weapons
found in the garage.
Physical evidence like
this is hard to beat.
The police are convinced
you aided the teacher
with his murders.
[AKECHI]
Kagami.
Show him the results
from the autopsy report.
He's a suspect.
That's against protocol.
I'm giving you permission.
[sighs] Okay, fine.
[MINAMI]
I'm Medical Examiner Minami!
And my name's Corpsey!
[BOTH] And this is your
Three-Minute Shocking!
Now! For today's corpse...
We have a thirty-year old male
who's been dismembered
and turned into art!
Which is pretty impressive
when you think about it.
It's unfortunate that
he died in his prime.
A strong sleeping agent was
found in his bloodstream,
but that wasn't the
ultimate cause of death.
Based on the crazy bruises we
discovered all over his neck,
choking is how this poor
sucker was murdered!
And after the killer offed him.
Then he was turned into a chair!
[CORPSEY]
How scary.
Judging by the bodies
found in the garage,
which were all
perfectly preserved,
the killer's become an
expert at their craft.
So that's kinda
spooky and gross.
[yells]
And here you have it--
a corpse arranged neatly
into a freaky chair.
Since doing all of this by hand
requires lots of
time and attention,
it would've needed to be
done in a private place
where the killer wouldn't've
been disturbed while he worked.
[CORPSEY]
Whoa, a chair.
Anyway, as we always say, kids,
don't try this at home, okay?
I'll see you at the next
Three-Minute Shocking!
There you have it.
That's the report from
the medical examiner.
So, one thing's clear, then.
The killer wanted the teacher
to die like his victims.
Hey, be honest, kid.
Are you sure you
weren't involved
in this thing in any way?
No, I swear, I wasn't.
But on the day the
teacher was murdered,
he'd called me in to see him
and I think the killer knew.
They knew I would be there
alone with the teacher,
so they framed me
for the murder.
Kobayashi! Why didn't
you tell us this before?
Sorry.
But I thought that I should
play my cards close to my chest.
I wanted to gather all of the
facts before I said anything.
You're unbelievable.
Don't you see?
I wanted to understand why the
killer was trying to frame me.
That's all.
I wanted a theory
before I told you.
And how do we know you're
not making all this up?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm...
[KAGAMI] Kobayashi, why did
your teacher call you in?
--Well, I think--
--[knocking]
[door clicks]
[POLICE]
Excuse me, sir.
What is it?
[POLICE] A boy claiming to be
the suspect's classmate is here.
He won't leave.
Says he has to see
him immediately.
[AKECHI]
Oh, him.
That kid's the sole heir
to the Hashiba Foundation.
Oh? Well, in that case, I guess
we can't just ignore him.
Show him through.
--Hey, you can come in now--
--[HASHIBA] Kobayashi!
--Hashiba!
--[HASHIBA] Are you okay?
Are they doing
terrible things to you?
Relax, kid.
You've seen one too
many bad police movies.
No, I'm fine.
Thanks for checking
on me, though.
No problem.
Well, then?
Did you do that thing
that I asked you to do?
Please, try.
Yeah.
And it looks like
your theory was right.
The real killer--
They're in our class.
I knew it! Thanks for your help.
Now I've got what I need.
Great. Fill me in.
Think you're ready to convince
me of your brilliance now?
Yes!
[KOBAYASHI] The day before
I found the teacher's body,
he called me in for
a meeting via email.
You can check
the email history
on my cell phone to verify.
My grades have never
really been all that bad.
And I've never done anything
that would get me into real
trouble with a teacher, either.
So, why then?
[TEACHER]
Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
Thanks for coming by.
I'm glad you did.
I've been thinking it over,
and I'm pretty sure I
haven't done anything
that would call for a
meeting with you, sir.
So, that means you wanted to see
me for personal reasons, right?
I guess you already know, then.
I'm a little embarrassed.
[KOBAYASHI]
So am I.
I'm so sorry, but I really
can't return your feelings.
[HASHIBA gasps]
Yup.
Turns out, our homeroom
teacher had feelings for me.
If you just stood around
flirting the whole time,
when was this murder supposed
to have been committed?
Right. I'm just imagining
what would've happened
if he had actually been
there for our meeting.
Just imagining?
[KOBAYASHI]
It actually happened like this.
By the time I arrived,
I think he had already
been murdered.
While I was standing
there in shock,
I believe the killer used
a strong sleeping agent
to knock me out.
After that, the killer hid
the teacher's dead body
behind the desk.
And they stuffed
me into a locker.
Then they waited it out
until the guard walked past.
[footsteps]
Once he'd made his final rounds,
the killer could do anything
they wanted until morning.
[KOBAYASHI] At that point,
they used a saw or something
to dismember the teacher's body
and turn him into
one of the chairs.
During all of that,
I was still sound asleep.
But later, after they were
finished with the teacher,
the killer made sure to put
my fingerprints on the tools
they brought from the garage
in order to frame me.
[HASHIBA] So you think
their plan was to frame you
from the very beginning?
Seems that way.
Your little tryst with
the teacher was a secret.
So, the killer would
have to be someone else.
Someone who could find
out when you'd meet.
[KOBAYASHI]
That's right.
Sure, but--
How'd you figure out who it was?
[KOBAYASHI]
Okay, stay with me here.
[KOBAYASHI] The house is
owned by the teacher's family,
but no one lives there now,
so he had total privacy.
But even so, it's strange that
such a long series of crimes
went unnoticed until now.
[HASHIBA]
That's true.
I think there's only one
thing that could explain it:
Our teacher and his victims
truly loved each other.
Wha--? No way!
Are you saying--?
Look at them.
They're all so beautiful.
Sure, I'll give you that.
The freak put some
care into his work.
[KOBAYASHI]
He created art with their bodies
because he was
obsessed with them.
And they cared
about him so much,
they actually
wanted him to do it.
The chairs were so beautiful.
It seemed like proof
that he loved them.
They thought,
"If I can be a chair,
I can be with him forever".
But this time, she made
him into a chair.
Either way, it's just insane!
[KOBAYASHI]
There was a reason the girl
he had gotten involved with
ended up turning on him.
[HASHIBA] So, what? Did she
begin to fear being killed?
Mm-mm. It was all
because of jealousy.
Huh?
Jealousy? How do you know?
Because she chose to
frame me for the crime.
He'd fallen out of love with
her and in love with me.
[KOBAYASHI] She was
humiliated and heartbroken
because she'd already
decided she wanted him
to turn her into
one of his chairs.
But then he left her because
of his feelings for me.
So, basically, I believe the
person who killed our teacher
and pinned the crime
on me was his girlfriend
until right before his death.
All of that might make
sense, theoretically,
but I still haven't
heard you prove that
you're actually innocent, kid.
But if Kobayashi
really is guilty,
then it's pretty strange that
his prints were only found
on the murder weapons and
nowhere else at the scene.
[NAKAMURA]
Well, there's a point.
[AKECHI]
If it were me,
I would've made sure
Kobayashi's fingerprints
were all over every
inch of that room,
from baseboards to doorknobs.
She really shouldn't have
half-assed the job like that.
[HASHIBA] Wait a minute,
just whose side are you on?
[AKECHI]
Nobody's.
She had assumed her first
crime would've been enough
to bring all of his
secrets to light.
That was her main goal,
so I don't think she
planned for much after that.
So then when she got
back to the garage...
What? She just panicked?
[KOBAYASHI] No. I think
she'd just reached her limit.
One thing's for sure.
It would've been easy
for a girlfriend
to check the email
history on his cell.
So finding time for the meeting
would've been no problem at all.
I imagine she probably had a
duplicate garage key, too, huh?
[HASHIBA sighs]
Thanks, Hashiba.
Because of your investigation,
I was able to confirm my theory.
Now all we have to do
is catch her in the act.
[metal scraping]
[door rattles]
[KOBAYASHI]
You were worried,
wondering why the
piece of evidence
you thought you took care
of was still here, right?
His cell phone hasn't turned up.
I'm sure that It's still
wherever you stashed it away.
That's not his.
Hashiba planted it
there to draw you out.
You're the real
murderer, aren't you...
...Hoshino?
You're the real murderer,
aren't you, Hoshino?
Why are you here, Kobayashi?
Shouldn't you be at home?
I thought something
was wrong with you.
No, I'm fine.
Everything's resolved now.
I see.
[KOBAYASHI] I never realized
how pretty you are, Hoshino,
even though we've
been in the same class
since elementary school.
But I see you differently now.
I can see the real you.
It's as clear as day.
You loved our teacher
very much, didn't you?
Still, though...
I had a feeling about you even
before we set up this trap.
[gasps]
That first day I
came back to school.
You, and only you, said
that our teacher's body
had been put into
a "crazy shape".
[HOSHINO]
Can you believe our teacher
was put into that crazy shape?
The teacher told you that he
was no longer in love with you,
so he had to break it
off, isn't that right?
[HOSHINO] When I could
see that my teacher's eyes
followed you every day,
my heart hurt so badly.
I began to obsess.
I hate Kobayashi.
I hate him.
I hate him!
You felt that way all this time.
He said since he no
longer loved me the best,
I couldn't be his chair.
He did say he was
really sorry, though.
He was always so
kind and gentle.
I was just an ordinary girl
who nobody ever cared about.
I was depressed and
lonely for so long,
I finally decided I
couldn't do it any more,
and I tried to kill myself.
But teacher stopped
me just in time.
He loved me.
[sobs]
He said he'd been watching me.
I might as well have been dead,
but he came into my life
and made me feel like
I really mattered.
I was so happy!
He said I could be his chair
so I could be with him forever!
But then, he took that
dream away from me!
[HOSHINO]
That's why I ended it this way.
It was all I could--
It was the only way
I could make him mine.
[KOBAYASHI]
I get it.
How are you standing there,
all calm and rational?!
Can't you feel? Why aren't
you furious with me?
I framed you for murder!
Why would I be angry?
It's the most fun I've ever had!
[HOSHINO gasps]
Don'tcha see?
This was my first time
attempting to solve a crime.
If you hadn't framed me, I
wouldn't have found my calling!
So... Thank you, Hoshino!
[HOSHINO cries]
[KAGAMI]
Kobayashi.
Mr. Kagami!
So does this mean that
we're all done here?
Yeah, as long as she cooperates.
If she tried to deny it now,
it would be a betrayal of
her love for our teacher.
And I don't think
she'd willingly do that.
You'll tell the truth from
here on out, right, Hoshino?
[HOSHINO] Now I know why he
was so drawn to you, Kobayashi.
He must have sensed
a kindred spirit.
You're really so much alike.
Well, that's not encouraging.
Well then? Is it over?
Yeah, looks like it finally is.
Thanks so much for
all of your help.
I'm sorry that I had to
ask you to put on an act.
I was so glad to help.
But it really blows
my mind that it was her.
I never thought it would
be one of the students.
[HASHIBA]
Yeah.
It makes me wonder about myself.
Am I brave enough
to teach at all?
[HASHIBA gasps]
Well, I believe you are, Miss!
[KAGAMI] Kobayashi,
we owe you an apology.
That was tremendous work today.
Oh, That's okay.
But don't you think it's time
we opened up this chair
to have a look inside?
I mean, it'll
obviously be evidence.
[KAGAMI]
What?
[KOBAYASHI]
It seems to me,
people usually want
their most precious things
kept close to them,
don't you think?
[KAGAMI, NAKAMURA gasp]
[KAGAMI]
Oh my god.
And he called this "love"?
[HANABISHI]
Ooh! What'd you find?
[screams]
[KOBAYASHI] After that,
Ms. Hanabishi wound up
taking a one-month
leave of absence.
[HASHIBA] I heard that
Hoshino officially confessed.
Her punishment will
be severe, won't it?
[AKECHI] Not as severe as being
turned into a literal arm chair.
It was you who arranged to have
Kobayashi released right away
when it first happened,
wasn't it, Akechi?
You did it so the real killer
would lose her patience.
[AKECHI]
Ugh, stop talking.
Seems to me Kobayashi was
used, and I don't like it!
Do you think I could
get some quiet, please?
[HASHIBA] I can't even begin to
understand someone like you!
It was Kobayashi who wanted to
solve the case, though, right?
[HASHIBA]
So what?! You put him in danger!
But why are you so upset?
[HASHIBA]
Anybody would be!
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm back!
Take your shoes off!
[KOBAYASHI]
I know!
[AKECHI]
Kagami, what do you think?
That garage would've been
discovered eventually, right?
[KAGAMI]
Yeah.
But the way the police operate,
it probably would've
taken a while.
Kobayashi blew us all away.
[HASHIBA]
So you're saying that Kobayashi
would've been released
sooner or later anyway?
[KAGAMI]
I think so.
Oh, I wouldn't be too sure.
He barely managed
to solve the crime.
It only went well because
the murderer gave herself up.
--[phone vibrates, rings]
--[KAGAMI] Uh-oh.
Is it a new case?
It's my little sister.
She's demanding that I come
home to visit her today.
It sounds like you should
probably get going.
Sister complex.
Hey, don't be a jack-ass.
Hashiba, I'll see you around.
'Kay.
As for you, try to
stay out of trouble.
You understand?
Mr. Kagami actually
seems like a nice guy.
[AKECHI]
Don't be fooled, kid.
It's impossible for
anyone to really know
another person's true nature.
Not that I give a crap.
[KOBAYASHI]
So? So? Did I really do it?
Akechi, did I pass?
[AKECHI sighs]
Yeah, just barely.
Hey, what's that?!
[KOBAYASHI giggling]
All right!
Kobayashi! I think you should
give this some more thought.
[KOBAYASHI] I don't have to
think! This is what I want!
This is who I am!
[gasps]
I feel...
...so alive!