[KOBAYASHI]
I was so bored with my life.
I couldn't stand it!
I wished reality would just end.
Then... All at once...
My life started changing.
--[rustling]
--[KOBAYASHI gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Hey, Akechi! Look!
Lemme just stop you right there.
What is that?
It's not what you think!
--Careful! Aw!
--[KITTEN meows]
See, it's a cat!
Someone abandoned her
at your front door!
[AKECHI gulps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Let's see.
The note says, "I thought a
detective agency could help.
Sorry to do this. Please
take her. She's sweet."
[AKECHI]
No.
We'll keep her here, okay?
[AKECHI]
Did you hear what I just said?
Yeah, but they don't
allow pets at my house.
[AKECHI]
Not my problem.
[AKECHI gasps]
Gotcha.
Not really a cat guy.
[KITTEN meows]
[HASHIBA] What? You're
actually gonna keep her?!
Yep! You don't mind
if she's here, right?
[HASHIBA]
Mm...
It's just that your last "pet"
was a cactus and you killed it.
Akechi's gonna take care of
her, so she'll be just fine!
[AKECHI] I don't recall
agreeing to any of this.
They're both big
meanies, aren't they?
[meows]
[HASHIBA] I've never known you
to be this into animals before.
[KOBAYASHI]
But look at her; she's so cute!
[HASHIBA]
Okay, listen.
Taking care of a living thing
comes with a lot of
responsibility, Kobayashi.
You can't rush into
things like this.
Well, what am I
s'posed to do with her?
Uh-- Uh...
[AKECHI]
Take her to the animal shelter.
But they'll kill her!
What kind of monster are you?
[AKECHI] Then find somebody
else who can take care of her.
[KOBAYASHI grumbles]
If you're determined to do this,
you can keep her at my house.
Hmm... But your parents.
They're so strict about
when you can have guests.
They wouldn't let
me come very often.
I'd hardly get to see her.
[HASHIBA]
Yeah, that's a good point.
Hey, guys? There's still
a cat in my apartment--
[meows]
[AKECHI gasps]
Demon!
Someone better get that
thing away from me right now!
I never pegged you
as a scaredy cat.
Pardon the pun.
I don't like
admitting I'm scared.
Stupid thing.
I know it must seem absurd.
But that's the way it is.
Okay. Then wouldn't it solve
the problem if you moved out?
If you say one more nonsensical
thing, I'm gonna beat you.
[HASHIBA]
You really hate cats, huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
I guess there's no choice.
We've got to find her a new
home where she'll be loved.
It all kinda feels
like the setup
to a mystery novel, doesn't it?
[AKECHI]
Shut up.
[meows]
Sorry, but you can't live here.
My boss is mean.
--Let's go.
--[KITTEN meows]
Who said you could put
that thing in my bag?
Now, say goodbye to
the cold-hearted man.
--[meows]
--[AKECHI] Would you just go?
[KOBAYASHI]
Okay, we'll see you later!
[SHADOW-MAN]
Hello, Kobayashi.
Beautiful day, huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
Mr. Shadow-Man! Hi!
[SHADOW-MAN] Sorry about this,
but I've got a bomb on me.
Think you could help?
[KOBAYASHI, HASHIBA]
A bomb?!
Wow, that's really fascinating.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Oh hey, Akechi!
--Shut up and go home.
--[SHADOW-MAN] Wait a minute--
[screams]
H-How do you expect
me to make it home
when I have a bomb
strapped to my chest?!
Don't care. Back to
your cardboard house.
[SHADOW-MAN]
This is my home--
[screams]
Why are you being so cold?
We're friends, aren't we?
I'd never associate
with you, criminal scum.
[SHADOW-MAN] Ahh! You act like
I'm some kind of troublemaker!
Maybe cuz you've got a
giant criminal record.
[SHADOW-MAN] Come on, man,
don't you have a heart?
--I'm a gentleman thief!
--No, I don't.
--Hashiba.
--Oh! Yes?
--Will you call the police?
--Yeah, good idea.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Wait! Hold on! Please!
Anything but that!
I'm begging you.
They'll arrest me!
So you understand the situation.
There's no harm in
letting him in, right?
He helped us out before.
Did you seriously
just call that "help"?
[SHADOW-MAN]
Thanks, Kobayashi!
Besides, that bomb
looks really powerful.
Mr. Shadow-Man might
be blown to bits!
[SHADOW-MAN]
Oh, so in other words,
you're really only curious
about the bomb, huh?
[SHADOW-MAN]
Freedom is wonderful.
Yep. And criminals
shouldn't be set free.
[SHADOW-MAN] It's all thanks to
you for defending me, Kobayashi.
Thank you.
Sure!
So, here we all are.
What are you gonna do now, kid?
Good question.
[SHADOW-MAN] Well, I happen
to be on my way home
from the video rental place.
Would you like to
watch a movie with me?
--Yay!
--[meows]
[AKECHI]
"Yay," my ass!
Here you go.
Anyone else?
[AKECHI]
Don't serve my precious coffee
to a piece of crap like him.
Could you please
just calm down?
[SHADOW-MAN]
So, Akechi.
I'd like to talk to you a
little bit about this bomb.
I don't care.
Come on, don't be like that.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Please, can't you do something?
Just leave when you
finish your drink.
[SHADOW-MAN] Okay. Well,
how about I stay a bit longer
and leave after the movie?
[AKECHI]
Watch it at 10 times speed.
But you guys...
Shouldn't we do something
about this before it gets
--too serious?
--Nope.
[KOBAYASHI] Is there any
chance it's just a prank?
[SHADOW-MAN]
That'd be great,
but considering that
these are people
who are capable of doing
this without my noticing,
I have my doubts.
Sounds like they're serious.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Exactly.
So do you think you
could help me, Kobayashi?
--[KITTEN meows]
--[AKECHI gasps]
[AKECHI sighs] I'm the one
who needs help around here!
[KITTEN meows]
[AKECHI sighs]
A gem? Emerald?
[SHADOW-MAN]
Verdict?
The worst-case scenario,
it's the real thing.
If it blows, it's gonna take
this entire floor with it.
Look, it says "GPS" on the side.
Fifty m slash three m?
What does that mean?
It has a distance limit.
[HASHIBA]
Wait. That means if he leaves--
If he leaves, it'll explode.
[HASHIBA]
Kobayashi, let's get outta here.
We'll go before it blows up.
Most of the wiring
is actually fake.
[HASHIBA] So you just have
to cut the real one, right?
But it's tricky.
If I take a guess and
cut the wrong wire,
we'll be dead in
the blink of an eye.
[HASHIBA]
Seriously, let's leave now.
[SHADOW-MAN]
What's the probability
of cutting the right one?
[AKECHI]
I'd say about one in thirty.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Well, I'll leave it to you.
No, you won't.
I'm not interested in having
my face blown off today, thanks.
[HASHIBA] Why don't you just
cut off the belt instead?
[AKECHI] They made it so
the bomb will detonate
if the belt is cut or
if heat's applied to it.
Well, it looks like we're gonna
need to call in an
expert after all.
Yep, I agree.
So how did you
manage to get a bomb
planted on you in
the first place?
[SHADOW-MAN]
I honestly don't recall.
The last thing I can
remember was checking out
at the counter at
the video rental shop.
And then, when I
woke up, I was here!
That video rental place
sounds a little suspicious.
You think you might have done
something to tick them off?
[SHADOW-MAN]
I've done nothing wrong.
You're kidding, right?
[SHADOW-MAN gasps] Are you
talking about my daily patrol
of the route elementary
girls take to school?
It makes me the portrait
of a good citizen.
[HASHIBA]
It makes you a creepy pervert.
[AKECHI] Enough. Just take
him to the police already.
[SHADOW-MAN] Now hold on
there a minute, Akechi.
If you abandon me now,
I'll be forced to tell
them about your bu--
[muffled scream]
You shut your mouth! How the
hell do you know about that,
--you piece of crap!
--[SHADOW-MAN] Whoa, whoa whoa!
I'm Shadow-Man,
master of disguise.
That's why.
As such, I can easily
access any secret I want.
You play dirty.
[KOBAYASHI] What were you
gonna say about Akechi?
Oh! He's got his childhoo--
Okay, you win. Not another
word from you, got it?
[BOTH]
What on earth is his secret?
[BABY cries]
[AKECHI]
What the...?
It's coming from the front door.
[ALL gasp]
Wow, it's a baby.
First a cat, then a bomb,
now a freakin' baby.
"This is your baby,
Detective, take care of her.
Please forgive me for
being a bad mother."
--[SHADOW-MAN] What?!
--[HASHIBA gasps]
So you're the baby's dad?
No!
[SHADOW-MAN]
But you're so young!
Did you hear me?
I don't know this kid!
Putting that question
aside for a minute.
Well, why's your place suddenly
being treated like an orphanage?
Who could be doing this to me?
[HOSTESS A] Hey, have you
guys heard the rumor that
that place is a
detective agency?
[HOSTESS B]
Seriously? That's so cool!
[HOSTESS C] Huh, maybe I'll
go ask them for some advice.
[HOSTESS A]
Why? You in trouble, Honey?
Yeah, it must be them.
[meows]
[AKECHI]
That's it. I'm moving.
[BABY laughs]
[KOBAYASHI]
There, there, Little One.
[SHADOW-MAN]
She's such a cute little thing.
Yeah!
[SHADOW-MAN] She'll grow
up to be a real beauty.
[KOBAYASHI]
How can you tell?
[SHADOW-MAN] When you watch
people as much as I do,
you can see it.
[KOBAYASHI]
Wow...
Hey. It's way too
crowded in here.
A perv, a bomb,
a cat, and a baby
should not be in the same
place at the same time, ever.
Why not?
[HASHIBA] I have to agree
with Akechi on this one.
All four of these issues
are jobs for the police.
Aw, things were just
getting exciting.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Indeed.
Dying in an explosion
is not exciting!
--[gunshot]
--[OFFICE WORKER screams]
That's gunfire!
Something must've
happened downstairs.
--[sirens]
--[ALL gasp]
[SHADOW-MAN]
Akechi! You're so cruel!
You really did call the police!
Believe it or not,
I actually didn't.
[EXTREMIST A]
Listen up!
We're the Tokyo Revolution!
Our goal is to overthrow
this corrupted government!
Now, where's our 300 million
yen and the getaway car?
--[OFFICE WORKER] Help!
--[EXTREMIST B] Shut up!
You've gotta be kidding me.
An armed robbery at
a time like this?
[POLICE]
You're completely surrounded!
Come out!
Surrender yourselves now!
[EXTREMIST A]
No surrender!
We're going to do
whatever it takes
to start a revolution
in this country!
I think this sounds
like terrorism.
[SHADOW-MAN] Nah, these guys
are just common thieves.
[BABY cries]
What a time for you
to start crying!
It's okay, Little One, don't
cry! Come on now, there there.
There there.
Stop crying.
[laughs]
[sighs] I hate children.
I hate cats, too.
And I really hate pervs.
[SHADOW-MAN]
She stopped crying.
Maybe she really is your child.
[AKECHI] Shut up or I'll
hand you over to the cops!
Forty minutes left.
--[gunshot]
--[ALL gasp]
[EXTREMIST A]
Where's the car we asked for?
This is bad, Akechi!
There's no way for us
to make it downstairs!
You're right.
Things couldn't get any worse.
[HASHIBA] Yeah, things
are officially worse.
I can't call the
company helicopter.
There are way too many
flight restrictions here.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Plus, it'd probably irritate
the charming thieves downstairs.
Why in the hell did
that moneylender
have to let this happen
today of all days?
Maybe they had some bad
karma coming their way.
Okay, is she hungry
or something?
Hashiba, go take a look inside
the bag that came with the baby.
[HASHIBA]
Oh, okay.
See if there's a
note or anything.
How does one prepare baby milk?
--[AKECHI sighs]
--[BABY burps]
What is it?
Are you completely sure
you're not her father?
[SHADOW-MAN]
Your apparent love affair
is very fascinating,
I assure you.
But do you think you could
direct your attention
to the bomb strapped
to my chest now?
I swear to god, you're the
very worst part of this day.
Hey, guys! I think I
just had a brilliant idea!
[KOBAYASHI]
Plan A!
Since I'm the smallest
among the group,
I'll hide here with the
baby and the kitten.
When the extremists
downstairs aren't looking,
you guys will make an attempt
to escape from the building.
Sneak your way down
towards the exit,
but just before you
make a run for it,
you cause a huge commotion
to attract their attention.
While they're distracted, I'll
evacuate the baby and the cat.
Oh! The hostage, too.
And then, just as soon as
we're clear, the bomb explodes!
[ALL]
What?!
[KOBAYASHI] All the bad guys
will go down in the blast!
Problem solved!
[SHADOW-MAN]
Huh. Yeah, that's a good idea.
Wait, no! Now I'm dead!
[AKECHI]
So are Hashiba and me.
[HASHIBA]
Kobayashi...
[AKECHI]
All right, my turn.
Here's plan B.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Let's hear it.
[AKECHI] You disguise yourself
as one of the extremists
and infiltrate their ranks.
An extra member will
cause some confusion,
which buys us both time
and an advantage.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Go on?
[AKECHI] We take that
opportunity to escape
via the emergency stairway.
Then, while they're still
figuring out what happened,
the bomb goes off.
The extremists will be
completely wiped out
and we'll be saved.
[SHADOW-MAN] Yeah, that
kills two birds with--
Wait. No. I'm dead again.
[KOBAYASHI]
That's a solid plan.
[AKECHI]
Right?
[SHADOW-MAN] Do either of
you have hearts at all?
[HASHIBA]
Okay, here's plan C.
How about we try
something like this?
We turn on every tap
on the entire floor
so that it floods with water.
--[faucet squeaks]
--[water flowing]
[HASHIBA] And in a dilapidated
old building like this,
it won't take long for
it to leak downstairs.
[AKECHI] We had some
trouble with that very issue
just the other day.
[HASHIBA] I know. I was the
one who had to apologize.
[AKECHI] Well, you learned
your lesson, right?
[HASHIBA] The next thing we're
going to need is a battery.
If I remember correctly,
there were three of
them up on the roof.
[AKECHI]
The motorcycle batteries.
Very observant of you.
I'm impressed.
[HASHIBA]
I remember you saying
you couldn't ride your
motorcycle anymore
because of all your
outstanding tickets.
[AKECHI] So what, now you're
memorizing everything I say?
That sounds neurotic.
I'm not neurotic!
Now. Here's the most
important part.
Mr. Shadow-Man will disguise
himself as law enforcement.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Ooh!
[HASHIBA] He brings the
battery in to the extremists
as if it were their
300 million yen.
Then, he puts the battery
down on the floor,
which is now totally flooded.
[HASHIBA] The extremists will
all get an electric shock.
Not only that,
there's a good chance
it'll make the bomb explode,
so they'll all be wiped out!
[SHADOW-MAN]
Aah! Splendid!
We're all splendidly deceased!
[HASHIBA]
Yeah, I guess that's not good.
Nope, not even close.
[AKECHI]
Okay, then.
We'll have to find a
different way to kill him.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Wait a minute!
Since when is that
the goal here?!
[SHADOW-MAN sighs] I really
should have known better
than to ask for
help from you guys.
[KOBAYASHI] It's really
livening up downstairs!
[HASHIBA]
How are you excited right now?!
Plan D. We have no choice.
We have to try to
unlock that belt.
[HASHIBA]
What?
[SHADOW-MAN]
Really?
[AKECHI]
Whoever took the trouble
to plant that bomb on you
specifically brought you to me.
It's obviously intended
as a challenge.
Someone out there wants
to see me squirm.
[HASHIBA]
Any idea who it might be?
It could be any
number of people.
So, the task is to figure out
who'd harass Akechi like this.
It's true.
There's probably a ton of
people who don't like him.
So the challenge is
to narrow it down.
[HASHIBA]
There are eight numbers.
If we make a
mistake, we're dead.
[KITTEN meows]
[KOBAYASHI] Could Mr. Shadow-Man
have staged this himself?
[SHADOW-MAN] Why would
I do something like that?
Well, maybe you wanted friends.
[SHADOW-MAN] Don't you
think it's pretty pathetic
if I have to go through this
much trouble to make friends?
[AKECHI] You are a pretty
pathetic guy, though.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Akechi!
If this is a challenge,
whoever did it must've
had a pretty good idea
that we wouldn't abandon
Mr. Shadow-Man, right?
[AKECHI scoffs] Sure,
'cause he's never caused us
any trouble or anything.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Right!
Well, present circumstances
excluded, of course.
[KOBAYASHI]
A present?
Wait, on the bomb,
there's a gem, isn't there?
An emerald!
[SHADOW-MAN]
Huh? Kobayashi?
Whoa. What?!
[HASHIBA]
Kobayashi!
[SHADOW-MAN]
What're you doing?
The emerald.
It's the birthstone for May.
[HASHIBA] Wait a minute.
That's today's date!
You unlocked it!
We did it!
--[AKECHI grunts]
--[BABY chirps]
[AKECHI growls, pants]
[yells]
[beeping]
--[EXTREMIST A] What was that?!
--[KOBAYASHI gasps] Akechi!
--Akechi, are you okay?
--[OFFICE WORKER screams]
--[sighs] Yeah.
--[POLICE, EXTREMISTS yelling]
[ALL]
Huh?
[HASHIBA]
What's that?
[KOBAYASHI] "Happy Birthday,
Black Lizard."
That bitch...
Wait, so she's
behind all this?
Does that mean you had
this baby with her?
Not a chance!
[phone rings]
Hello? Yeah, he's
sitting right here.
You wanna talk to him? Okay.
What?
[KOBAYASHI]
Somebody wants to talk to you.
[BLACK LIZARD]
Surprise! Happy birthday to me!
[AKECHI]
Black Lizard.
[BLACK LIZARD]
That's right!
You didn't forget my
birthday, did you?
You're a brilliant detective--
of course you remembered it!
Right? Right?
Absolutely not. I erased
it from my memory
the moment I placed
you under arrest.
[BLACK LIZARD moans]
You didn't remember?
Oh, of course you didn't,
you little tease!
If this whole thing was
some kind of surprise party,
that's messed up.
[SHADOW-MAN]
Oh, I get it!
The clerk at the
video rental shop
was somehow in cahoots
with Black Lizard, huh?
[KOBAYASHI]
So, Ms. Black Lizard.
You used the baby to
stage all of this?
[BLACK LIZARD]
A baby? It's mine? With Akechi?
I mean, I've imagined
it so many times!
You're saying it
finally came true?
It's like she eats
stupid for breakfast.
[KOBAYASHI]
What about the cat?
[BLACK LIZARD] A cat?
There's a little kitty there?
Okay, what about the robbery?
[BLACK LIZARD] Robbery? No, I
don't know anything about that.
So the baby, the cat,
and the robbery
weren't connected at all? Wow.
[SHADOW-MAN]
What a strange coincidence.
Like all the planets
lining up at once.
[BABY cries]
Can you please take her, Akechi?
[AKECHI sighs]
Stop crying, 'kay?
Weird day.
[AKECHI] A cat, a baby,
a bomb, and terrorist thieves.
I think my head's
gonna ache for a week.
Stop impersonating me!
Oh, Akechi!
I didn't see you there!
Go home.
[SHADOW-MAN] Of course!
Right after I watch this DVD!
Spoiler alert:
the annoying bag-head pervert
dies in the end.
[HASHIBA]
Well, Kobayashi.
I think it's time to take
the baby to the police.
--[KOBAYASHI sighs] Okay...
--[knocking]
You've got to be kidding me.
[KOBAYASHI]
Coming!
[HOSTESS C]
Um. Hi.
[HASHIBA]
Hello...
--May I ask who you are?
--[HOSTESS C gasps]
Oh, it's my baby!
[KOBAYASHI]
Are you really her mother?
I'm so sorry.
I heard a rumor this
was a detective agency
that helped people in trouble,
and that you never
turned anyone away.
Where the hell would
anyone get that idea?
Is there any way
you can convince us
this baby belongs to you?
[HASHIBA]
Do you have any kind of proof
that she's your daughter?
Some proof?
Yes, the birthmark!
She has a tiny, sort of
heart-shaped birthmark
right on her bottom!
[SHADOW-MAN]
Look, it's just like Ake--
[screams]
[sobs] I left her on impulse.
I only wanted my freedom.
I'm sorry...
--[HOSTESS C] Sweet love.
--[BABY laughing]
There, there.
Please don't ever
abandon her again.
What? No, of course I won't!
Don't say "of course."
You already abandoned her once.
[HOSTESS C gasps]
Kobayashi...
I think that's enough.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I'll go.
[KITTEN meowing]
[KOBAYASHI chuckles]
[KOBAYASHI]
I'll never abandon you, Kitty!
[KITTEN meows]
It seems like she's
completely settled in now.
You know that's because
you keep feeding her, right?
I promised that I
wouldn't abandon her!
--[HASHIBA] Is it good, Kitty?
--[AKECHI] Hey!
I never said you could
keep that thing here.
But permission from a human
doesn't mean
anything to kittens.
[KITTEN meows]
[AKECHI gasps]
Hey! Don't come any closer!
I mean it!
Besides, I think she
actually likes you
more than anyone else, Akechi!
[AKECHI] Don't even
think about touching me!
[NAKAMURA]
So... How's it going?
You like jerky, right?
Oh, and I brought you
some magazines, too.
I appreciate it.
But I told you not
to worry about me.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
Look, Kagami.
You should know.
Since you've been here,
there've been more
Twenty Faces murders.
It's exactly like you predicted.
They say they're
punishing criminals
in lieu of the
good-for-nothing police.
We're working our butts off down
at the precinct too, you know.
But I'm really strugglin' here.
I'm not sure anymore what the
right side is-- You or us.
I feel like I'm going nuts!
[KAGAMI]
Mr. Nakamura.
Please don't become like me.
I beg you not to screw
your life up like I did.
I really don't think
I could stand it.
Stay strong.
Be that veteran officer
I admire. Don't change.
Well then. I'll see
you next time.
[KAGAMI]
Thank you, my friend.