[KOBAYASHI groans]
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
Is that Teacher?
[KOBAYASHI]
In that moment,
I knew that my boredom
had come to an end.
[KAGAMI]
Good morning, Officer.
So, that him?
[POLICE A]
Yes, sir.
[KAGAMI]
I'll take it from here.
[POLICE B]
Yes, sir.
[KAGAMI] Well, young man, looks
like you're our key witness.
I hope you plan to cooperate.
Aren't I a suspect, though?
We haven't ruled it out.
Though at a glance,
my gut tells me
you're just a pawn
in all of this.
[HASHIBA]
Please let me through!
[POLICE B]
You can't go in!
Kobayashi!
Hey, Hashiba.
[POLICE C]
Hold it!
Tell them there's no way
that you're the murderer!
I already did.
But when I woke up I
was the only one here.
But you had no reason for
killing the teacher, Kobayashi!
[POLICE C]
If you wanna make a statement
of your own, we can
take you in, too!
Alright, then! Fine,
I'll go in with him.
[POLICE C]
Who are you, kid?
I'm his best friend,
got it? He needs me!
[NAKAMURA] You're going to
have to do better than that.
Okay. I'm also his
class representative
and the President of
the Student Council.
I need to be able to
explain what's happened
to the other students.
[NAKAMURA] Well, at least
you're more on the ball
than your teachers.
But getting involved in this
case would be a mistake.
Go on, kid, go home.
[POLICE C]
You heard him!
[HASHIBA]
Let go!
[AKECHI]
What's the problem?
[POLICE C] Hey! This area's
off limits to students!
[KAGAMI]
Oh, he's okay.
[POLICE C]
Huh?
I asked him to come help out.
He's a licensed detective,
believe it or not.
[POLICE C gasps]
Sorry! My mistake.
--Imperial Household Agency.
--[HASHIBA] A detective?
[AKECHI]
This headache is killin' me.
So... Dismembered body of
a homeroom teacher, huh?
Very showy. I like it.
[KAGAMI] Don't be morbid in
front of the students, Akechi.
[AKECHI] Gotta say, this
looks pretty bad for you, kid.
[KOBAYASHI gasps]
Well, I'll just have to
prove I didn't do it.
And how're you gonna
do that, enlighten me.
By proving who did. Sir.
[door clicks, creaks]
I appreciate you coming
in to talk today.
[KOBAYASHI] Well,
considering that I was found
holding the murder weapon,
it's completely natural
for you to be suspicious.
Y'know, kid,
you're awfully calm.
Shouldn't I be?
So, do you still think
Kobayashi's guilty?
[sighs] Officially,
he's still a suspect.
But personally, I'm
inclined to believe you.
[NAKAMURA] You're lucky
you aren't of age, kid.
If you were, we would've
had to keep you here
until we were finished
with the investigation.
[KOBAYASHI]
Lucky me.
--[NAKAMURA laughs]
--[HASHIBA] Come on,
your parents are waiting.
Crazy. There goes
our prime suspect.
You really feel okay about
releasing him like this?
We're following
Akechi's instructions.
Aah... the young
detective strikes again.
Seems a nice kid.
Hard to imagine he could have
done something like that.
Killing his homeroom teacher.
Well, they're definitely out
there, though-- Messed up kids.
You'd have'ta be naïve
to think they're not.
Right.
[NAKAMURA]
That came out wrong!
Forgive me, Superintendent.
I was out of line.
No, Nakamura, you're right.
We can't rule anything out.
[STUDENT A] They still haven't
found the killer, right?
[STUDENT B] Come on,
it was obviously the kid
who was in the classroom!
[STUDENT A]
Hey, look!
[STUDENT B]
Seriously?
[STUDENT C] I can't believe
he's back at school already!
[STUDENT D]
If I was the new teacher,
I would not be good with that.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Morning!
[STUDENT E]
Hey, Hashiba.
[STUDENT F]
So, um, is it true that
Kobayashi's the one who, uh...
There's no need to worry.
I was with him when he
went to the station.
They said they don't
believe he did it.
[STUDENT F]
Oh, okay.
[STUDENT E] Yeah, I guess
if you're cool with him.
[HASHIBA]
You okay?
Don't listen to them, all right?
Oh, it's fine.
Doesn't bother me.
[HASHIBA gasps]
Well, that's good.
I mean, I get why they're upset.
After all, the suspect
is still among them.
But don't worry.
Once I figure out who
the real killer is,
hopefully, everyone will
be able to move on.
[door rattles]
[HANABISHI]
Okay, Children, time for class!
Everyone, take
your seats, please!
Oh, are you going to
be our new teacher?
[HANABISHI]
I sure am!
And you must be Hashiba,
the class rep!
--[HASHIBA] Uh, yes.
--[HANABISHI] Well, my name is
Ms. Hanabishi, and I'm
so pleased to announce
that I'll be your homeroom
teacher, starting today!
I know you've all been
through quite a scare,
but I truly believe we can
get through this
trying time if we all
--pull together!
--[KOBAYASHI] The reason
the killer arranged the
body so deliberately
was because they were trying to
say the teacher deserved to die.
[KOBAYASHI]
When I woke up, it was morning.
Before that, I'd fallen
asleep in class.
No, it was more like I
had been put to sleep.
I must have been, huh?
I can't think of another reason
I would've spent the
whole night here.
The person who did it
had to be in a position
to frame me for the murder.
That's right. The killer
is someone who knows me
--fairly well.
--[HASHIBA] Kobayashi.
[HANABISHI] I don't have
many friends, so please
--don't hestiate...
--[HASHIBA] What do you think?
New teacher's quite a character.
[HANABISHI] And I can help
you with your schoolwork
any time at all!
You guys are pretty smart--
you should be able to make up
--for lost time quickly, right?
--Yeah, quite.
[bell chimes]
[HANABISHI]
Oh, Kobayashi!
You poor little thing.
I hope you know I'm here
if you need to talk.
This must have been
such an ordeal for you!
That's really nice of you.
Thank you very much,
Ms. Hanabishi.
[HANABISHI gasps]
It's my pleasure!
Get this. You're going
to die laughing--
I totally thought you were
a girl when I saw you!
Believe me, I get
that all the time.
[STUDENT G]
Yeah, he's cuter than we are!
[STUDENT H] Even though he's
a boy; it's totally not fair.
[HOSHINO]
We all thought he was a girl
in elementary school, too!
He used to get embarrassed.
Remember?
Aw, is that true, Kobayashi?
--[KOBAYASHI chuckles]
--Aww! How sweet!
I'm so jealous of you
cute, young things!
[HASHIBA] Hey! What do
you think you're doing?!
[HANABISHI giggles] Sorry,
it's my first day as a teacher
and I tend to get a little bit
huggy when I'm nervous!
Anyhoo, see you tomorrow!
[STUDENT G] Ms. Hanabishi, I
love your outfit! It's so cute!
[HANABISHI] Oh, thank you,
Sweetie! How's the rest of me...
[HOSHINO] Our new teacher's
a little weird, isn't she?
Yeah, she is. But at least
she seems really nice.
Yeah, she's just
overcompensating
because of all the
pressure she's feeling.
[HASHIBA]
You think so?
[KOBAYASHI]
She's taking over in a class
where a murder was committed.
[HOSHINO]
Can you believe our teacher
was put into that crazy shape?
[HASHIBA] I know...
I really liked him, too.
[HOSHINO]
Yeah, so did I. It's a shame.
I-I'm sorry. I gotta go.
[HASHIBA]
Uh, see you tomorrow.
Where exactly is it that
we're going right now?
You'll see. Thanks
for coming with me.
Yeah, no problem.
[KOBAYASHI]
I decided something.
[HASHIBA]
And what's that?
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm going to do it.
[HASHIBA]
Huh? Do what?
[KOBAYASHI]
What do you think?
What he does.
[HOSTESSES chattering]
[KOBAYASHI, HASHIBA panting]
[HASHIBA] They should
fix the freaking elevator.
[yelps]
Mr. Detective, are you in there?
Please open the door!
I can't remember ever seeing him
this interested
in anything before.
Answer me!
Wanna just... go?
[door clicks, creaks]
You shouldn't be here.
But here I am.
[AKECHI] How'd you find
this place, anyway?
I got the idea
at the station.
I saw your call come in on
the detective's cell phone.
I knew that number
belonged to this area.
When I checked, I found out
it was the number for a store
in this neighborhood
that closed a while back.
But when I asked a real
estate agency about it,
they said there was
still an office here.
And here I thought I was clever.
[KOBAYASHI]
It was just a hunch, really.
But as soon as we got here,
I knew this had to
be the right place.
[AKECHI]
That's some hunch.
[HASHIBA]
Kobayashi!
[AKECHI]
So, if I'd used a cell,
you wouldn't have
been able to find me.
Oh, and take your shoes off.
[KOBAYASHI]
Do you even have one?
I noticed that you
weren't carrying one
while you were investigating
the crime scene,
so I figured you probably don't.
Aren't you the observant one?
You're right, I'm not
into cell phones.
[HASHIBA] You have a
computer, though, right?
Of course I do, you can't
play SimCity without one.
[HASHIBA gasps]
Oh, wow. Is this the stuff
you use to solve crimes?
[AKECHI]
Don't move anything.
It's all right where
it's supposed to be.
[KOBAYASHI]
I totally get that.
[HASHIBA] It's supposed
to look this way?
I think that's the oldest
couch I've ever seen.
Yeah, well, it belonged
to the previous owner.
It's the only thing he
left behind that I like.
[gasps]
[AKECHI] That's all I've got
to drink-- you're welcome.
If you want something else,
I hope you brought
it with you. Hm?
[AKECHI sighs]
So, uh... "Akechi."
That's your name, right?
You're enrolled at
Kabuki-cho High School.
I checked into you, too.
Come to find out, you're some
kind of an urban legend.
You scored 100% on all
the entrance exams,
but you haven't attended
school even once
since the opening ceremonies.
And yet, you haven't
been expelled.
[AKECHI]
I'm an Agency-authorized
specially designated minor
with an attendance waiver.
What does that mean?
I've basically got permission
from the government
to skip school. See?
But why? Are you
sick or something?
[AKECHI]
Nope, I'm quite healthy.
Oh, then is it, like, some
kind of a mental disorder?
What do you think?!
Uh, no, I guess not.
[AKECHI]
I get special allowances
because I've put my
considerable talents
at the government's disposal.
What talents?
Your skills as a
detective, right?
Right. I'm not too surprised you
haven't heard of the program.
Few people have.
It's just one of many
the government's set up
to attract "gifted youth."
They're not
publicized, of course,
because it's clearly favoritism
and it violates
the Constitution.
But they exist.
They've been recruiting
young talent for decades.
Otherwise those with
special abilities
would remain unutilized.
It's in the national
interest to use us.
At least, that's
a convenient excuse
to justify bending a few rules.
Who am I to argue?
[HASHIBA]
That's ridiculous.
[AKECHI] Amazing how easily
people are conditioned
to ignore the obvious,
even when the truth is staring
them right in the face.
Don't you think,
Young Master Hashiba?
[HASHIBA gasps]
[AKECHI]
I did my own research.
Bright young Souji Hashiba,
heir to the huge conglomerate,
the Hashiba Foundation.
And, once you get
to take over...
[AKECHI] You'll learn quickly
how the world really works,
whether you like it or not.
You'll see.
[HASHIBA]
Yeah, I'll take it over.
But I know I'll never
take part in anything
that's unfair, dishonorable,
or deceptive.
Is that so?
Anyway, it was you over there
who wanted to see me, right?
So, what do you want from me?
One thing, to be your assist--
[AKECHI]
No assistants.
Kobayashi!
[KOBAYASHI]
You wouldn't have to pay me.
[AKECHI]
No volunteers either, okay?
Go home, kid.
[KOBAYASHI]
I can't.
This is the first time
anything's felt fun for me.
No matter what mystery games
I play or books I read,
they don't help. I'm still
bored and unsatisfied.
I feel empty.
But now our
teacher's dead,
and it looks like I'm
the primary suspect.
And suddenly, my life
feels really fun!
Kobayashi...
Feels fun, huh?
That's a pretty naïve
point of view.
And you know what they say
about curiosity and the cat.
But if you don't
really feel alive,
what's the point of living?
What're you even saying?
[AKECHI]
Hmph.
[AKECHI sighs]
[AKECHI]
No matter what I take,
the pain doesn't go away.
[AKECHI sighs]
Otherwise, what's
the point of living?
[AKECHI]
Here's the thing, kid.
They're still extremely
suspicious of you.
[KOBAYASHI]
I don't care about them.
You're convinced
that I didn't
have anything to
do with it, right?
[AKECHI]
Yeah, sure I am.
But it's been a whole week now.
My bet is: the real killer's
about to lose patience
and start looking for attention.
[HASHIBA]
You think so?
[KOBAYASHI]
It does make sense
that they would want to be
acknowledged for their work.
[HASHIBA]
Why?
[AKECHI] No murderer would
go through that much trouble
if they weren't trying
to make a point.
They were hoping to create
a spectacle, a show.
The goal was to make
a splashy headline.
But that hasn't happened,
so now they're
getting frustrated.
They're pissed that
nobody's talking about it.
[HASHIBA gasps]
You restricted the media!
Damn right, I did.
I made sure the murder didn't
get so much as a
word of coverage.
Your school went right back to
business as usual, too, right?
[HASHIBA] Is that thanks to
your "special arrangement"?
They've given you
quite a lot of power
for your age, haven't they?
No doubt.
You catch on fast, kid.
Still though,
it's not hard to do.
The general public doesn't
pay much attention
to the news to begin with.
Not unless it affects them.
And you can be certain
they won't go out of
their way to seek it out.
It's easier to glide along,
living in a state of
blissful ignorance.
That seems pretty harsh.
[AKECHI]
Passionate type like you
is actually much more rare.
[AKECHI]
Now, don't get me wrong,
I'm no better than
the rest of them.
I don't do this job
for any noble reason.
And I don't care how
gruesomely people die.
[AKECHI] I solve abnormal crimes
for the thrill of the game.
[HASHIBA]
You're disgusting.
Hey, thanks, man.
[AKECHI, HASHIBA gasp]
Kobayashi...
[AKECHI]
You okay there, kid?
I wanna be like you!
[gasps]
[AKECHI] Okay. Then let's
play a little game.
If the perpetrator's still
out there, then go find them.
Go solve this case.
Let's see if you can do that.
If you do, then I'll
admit you've got talent.
And your life will
change forever.
The people in charge will
start calling on you.
But who knows?
Maybe that'll be just the thing
to cure some of that boredom.
This is crazy.
Kobayashi! This guy's
only gonna get you killed!
We're outta here!
'Kay. Just one more
thing, though.
Forgot to tell ya.
There's a new arrest warrant
out for you, Kobayashi.
Turns out, your teacher
was a homicidal maniac.
They found some
fascinating new evidence.
You're suspected of
being an accomplice,
so it's back to
square one for you.
--[door clatters]
--[HASHIBA gasps]
[HASHIBA ]
You called the police?!
[AKECHI]
No, I emailed them.
There's a suspect
in my living room.
What'd you expect?
Hey! Take off your shoes!
Hello, Kobayashi.
So, you are here.
Mr. Kagami.
[NAKAMURA]
I'm afraid your fingerprints
have been found on
several murder weapons
recovered from the victim's
parents' house, Kobayashi.
[KOBAYASHI]
The victim's parents' house?
Do you mean... our teacher?
Here, have a look.
Wait, are those--
What is that?
[NAKAMURA]
This is the scene we came upon
at your murdered
teacher's parents' house.
[KAGAMI] We found multiple
bodies in the garage,
along with several murder
weapons with your prints.
[KOBAYASHI]
Human chairs.
[KAGAMI] It would appear that
your teacher was a killer
long before he was a victim.
This is his work.
[NAKAMURA]
He was a mass murderer
who apparently also
happened to be into
do-it-yourself home
improvement projects.
Kobayashi...
I didn't want to
believe it of you,
but the evidence
can't be ignored.
[HASHIBA gasps]
No!
You knew about this the
whole time we were here
and you kept us from leaving!
Kid, just how do you figure
that I kept you from leaving?
I told you both to go home.
You guys were persistent.
You were determined to stay.
Besides...
The harder the game, the more
thrilling it is to play,
am I right, Kobayashi?
You're a--
Yes, I agree.
Much more thrilling.
What are you saying?
The game...
...begins now.