[NAMIKOSHI]
So, Akechi.
What do you think?
It's brilliant, but reckless.
Complex systems.
Is this Chaos theory?
Yes, that's right, but
it's just the beginning.
The fundamentals involved
are quite similar,
but the goal of my formula
is to ascertain the future.
I'm creating a program that
predicts every possible position
of all matter in the
world at any given time.
[AKECHI]
Intriguing.
But, how will it be
able to reconcile
with quantum mechanics?
Uh! That must be why
you're using Chaos Theory.
[NAMIKOSHI]
Mm-hm. Exactly.
My goal is to create
Laplace's Demon.
I'd like my demon to assist
in altering the future.
Intervening in tangible ways.
Then the first thing
to do is give it a name.
A name?
This demon's your
own creation.
It doesn't make sense to
borrow someone else's.
[NAMIKOSHI gasps]
[NAMIKOSHI] Then, what
do you think of this one?
An omniscient law to shed
light on the dark world.
"Dark Star."
[HASHIBA gasping]
[KOBAYASHI gasping]
[AKECHI]
There's only one thing left.
What was the motivation
behind the murders?
[KOBAYASHI] Have you really
figured out everything else?
[AKECHI]
Pretty much.
A company creates a theme
park, Panorama Island.
Then two high-profile
men were found dead.
[AKECHI]
Eccentric dreamers.
They were partners
who conceived the idea
and followed it through.
This morning,
the Shinjuku Metropolitan
Police received a challenge:
An invitation to solve
an impossible crime
on Panorama Island.
It was, without a doubt,
sent by Twenty Faces.
It's not an accident.
They were murdered.
[MINAMI]
I'm Medical Examiner Minami!
And I'm Corpsey!
[BOTH] It's time for
Three-Minute Shocking!
[MINAMI] I'm back again
with some useful info!
We already covered
the cause of death
was either crushing
or suffocation,
but details are important
so let's take a closer look!
We have to do it again?
[MINAMI]
There are two victims,
Genzaburo Komoda
and Hirosuke Hitomi!
Do you really need
two of us for this?
One is probably enough!
It helps with the effect.
[MINAMI]
The murderer called these two
into the exhibition hall,
and, three, two, one!
[ALL scream]
[MINAMI]
There ya have it!
That's it for today's
Three-Minute Shocking!
Am I missing something?
There's nothing new!
[MINAMI] The fact that
the victims were called
into the exhibition hall
is essential to the case!
If someone lured them in knowing
that everything was about
to fall, it's obviously a
mannequin manslaughter!
In conclusion, I
believe that this was
a premeditated murder by someone
who anticipated the collapse!
See you next time!
[AKECHI] I'm assuming this
gear is part of a larger set
of mechanical systems
used in the hall?
It just might be.
The entire exhibition hall
has motorized parts installed
in the ceiling.
Take a look up there.
We were eventually going
to run electricity to it.
[KOBAYASH] Were all of
these going to move?
[TSUNODA]
Yeah, that was the plan.
Why, even the largest ones were
designed with a purpose in mind!
[TSUNODA]
Charmain Komoda and Mr. Hitomi
wanted them to look as
if they were dancing!
I've never seen anything
like this before!
Maybe... the collapse was
caused by a loose bolt,
or some other flaw
in the machinery
that moved the mannequins?
[NAKAMURA]
Any possibility of malfunction?
[TSUNODA]
No, sir, absolutely not!
We had teams of architects
and engineers who perfected
the design of this area. Right?
Uh. Yes. The blueprints were
checked multiple times.
Every mechanism in this room
is made of the highest
quality materials available.
Then explain this.
[ALL gasp]
It snapped like a twig!
Structures are as strong
as their weakest parts.
These flimsy gears are useless.
[TSUNODA, KITAMI, MIYAMA]
Uh...
[AKECHI] Who was responsible
for ordering the metal?
[KITAMI]
Well it was...
[ALL]
Mm?
[AKECHI] Office worker
Chiyoko Higashikoji.
Yes.
[AKECHI] So you're admitting
that you purposely
chose weak materials?
I can explain.
[HASHIBA]
Ms. Higashikoji is the killer?
That doesn't make any sense!
[AKECHI]
And why not?
Look, I understand the fact
that the metal is weak,
but how could she predict
the specific time
the machinery would collapse?
[KOBAYASHI] It's just math.
You can calculate it.
Calculate it, huh?
Are you really saying that to me
when you skipped the math exam?
[AKECHI] It's a question
of having the right tools.
A little knowledge of math and
a computer would be enough.
If someone has a degree
in both mechanical and
material engineering,
it'd be child's play.
Confiscate Higashikoji's
computer.
[NAKAMURA]
I'm already on it.
Did ya get that?
Okay, good...
[KOBAYASHI] You know
what's interesting to me?
They're a little creepy
hanging up there like that.
But I can't help but notice
how beautiful they are!
Huh? What the heck
are you talking about?
[KOBAYASHI]
Don't they seem familiar?
Take a look at our suspect.
Uh! Yeah, do you mind telling me
exactly what you're
getting at here?
[KOBAYASHI] I'm saying she
has a beautiful body!
[HASHIBA]
Uh...
[HIGASHIKOJI whimpers]
[HASHIBA gasps]
[KOBAYASHI]
Now, look up there.
[HASHIBA] Uh! I still
don't know what I'm...
[gasps]
[HASHIBA]
They have her... face?
[KOBAYASHI]
Her face, her body.
This woman is the model
for all the mannequins
in the exhibition hall.
Isn't that correct?
[HASHIBA gasps]
[AKECHI]
Chiyoko Higashikoji,
is the existence of
this exhibition hall
your motivation for murder?
It's more than that.
There sure are a lot of you.
Was it frightening to
see them all here?
I think this kind of thing
would frighten anyone,
but is it enough to
kill people over?
You're right.
I killed them.
I hate it here!
I can't stand this room!
There's more though.
The secrets...
I just couldn't bear
the pain anymore.
[HIGASHIKOJI] It's true that
Komoda and Hitomi were
highly esteemed men in society,
but behind the scenes, they
made such callous sacrifices.
My friend, Yukiko Tezuka,
was only one of many.
Yukiko.
[HIGASHIKOJI] For weeks she'd
been forced to work over 20
hours a day. She had to
push herself to the point
of exhaustion or risk dealing
with the consequences.
She was so frail.
Her health was declining daily.
I didn't know what
to do for her.
[cries]
[HIGASHIKOJI]
And then, she died.
Listen to me!
The least you could do is
apologize to her parents!
Chairman! Producer!
I'm impressed.
[HITOMI]
Yes, it's wonderful!
[KOMODA] We're a huge entity
that she'd normally be unable to
stand up to, but because of the
love for her dear companion.
[HITOMI] She dares to rise
fearlessly against us!
How courageous!
What a noble spirit!
My dear, there is no
doubt that you are....
[HIGASHIKOJI gasping]
[KOMODA, HITOMI] The ideal woman
that we have been searching for.
Our goddess to revere!
Don't do this. No!
[KOMODA]
You are truly the best, Chiyoko.
[HITOMI]
I never expected
that you'd have such
a beautiful body!
[KOMODA]
We agree to apologize
to the family of the
dead office worker.
We'll compensate them as well,
if it would please you.
[HITOMI] However, you must agree
to sign a contract with us.
Sign a contract?
She sold her body
to those men.
[HIGASHIKOJI]
They promised improvement.
I'll sign, if this is
what it will take.
[whimpers] I will give them...
my body.
[HIGASHIKOJI]
Why?!
The working conditions for
the Panorama Island project
are worse than before!
Nothing has changed
since Yukiko died!
[HITOMI]
Look what we've done, Chiyoko!
[KOMODA] It's a tribute to
display our devotion to beauty.
The fruit of our love!
[HITOMI]
This is an island made
to celebrate
everything about you!
[KOMODA] We were searching
for the perfect model
while we constructed
Panorama Island.
With you as our muse,
we can now complete the
island's focal point,
the mannequin exhibition hall,
in a most timely manner!
You will be worshiped
by millions,
and you will belong
to us forever!
Was it worth it, Yukiko?
With the money they
made from your work,
they created... so many.
They forced you to work
yourself to death.
And then...
They say I'm a goddess.
It's not fair!
[HIGASHIKOJI] I wanted to do
whatever I could to help those
who had no voice.
But I didn't change anything.
My body belongs to them now
and the employees still suffer.
Oh, Yukiko.
Did you know about
this from the start?
It was obvious.
So really, we did just
need to find the motive.
It's actually a simple case.
A woman sold herself to the two
demons who killed her friend.
To beat them, she became
a demon herself.
[HIGASHIKOJI]
It's true.
I murdered Chairman Komoda
and Mister Hitomi.
I'm the Twenty Faces
of Panorama Island.
[KAGAMI] Twenty Faces is on
the rise. You can't stop it.
When fueled by injustice,
the innocent can become
murderous vigilantes.
I don't understand why
she posed as Twenty Faces
and sent that letter.
The island's authorities
would have called the
murders an accident.
She wanted someoneto know.
What?
Her truth.
Sometimes beautiful things
are built through ugly means.
She wanted people to see
all of the sacrifices
that went into making
this beauty possible.
She's our fourth
Twenty Faces this month.
I wouldn't be surprised to
see multiple crimes like this
happening all at once.
If it ever gets to that,
there's no way you'll be able
to deal with them all alone.
If more Twenty Faces are out
there, I'll crush them all.
[NAKAMURA]
What?!
You can't send a helicopter?
Boat?
Oh, I understand.
[KOBAYASHI]
We can't be going home already!
We just got here.
I wanna swim!
Don't you?
[HASHIBA]
Well, I don't have a suit,
plus we don't have
time right now.
The boat is on the way.
[KOBAYASHI] I don't see
it yet. Just a quick dip!
Why are you doing that?!
Once the exam is over,
I'll take you to the beach
or anywhere you want to--
[AKECHI] You take good
care of him, Hashiba.
[HASHIBA]
Uh? I do?
[KOBAYASHI] Ms. Higashikoji.
She loved Yukiko.
It almost seems honorable
to kill for friendship, huh?
Well, I guess it could be,
since she was trying
to avenge her death.
Uh?!
[KOBAYASHI]
Hey, Hashiba!
If I was ever murdered,
would you make a vow
to avenge my death?
Why would you even
ask that? I dunno.
I guess I'd just do
everything that I could
to keep you from dying.
Hey, no fair! It's a
yes or no question!
[HASHIBA]
Well, I'm saying I'd do my best
to make sure I never have
to make that choice.
[KOBAYASHI]
Mm?
[HASHIBA growls]
Even if I did avenge your death,
you wouldn't be
able to come back.
[KOBAYASHI]
I see.
[HASHIBA] Why would you even
ask a question like that?
[KOBAYASHI]
Just curious.
[HASHIBA]
Well, cut it out.
I don't even like thinking
about that stuff.
[KOBAYASHI]
Akechi, we made it home!
[AKECHI sighs] So you're
calling my place home now.
Hard not to!
We've been coming here every
day since exam week started.
Take this as a token
of our appreciation.
[KOBAYASHI] We actually
didn't come here yesterday.
[HASHIBA] That's because
we flew to an island.
I guess that's true.
[HASHIBA] By the way,
just thought I'd mention,
I know you skipped
the English test today.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm...?
You slipped away after lunch.
Did you really think I wouldn't
notice that you disappeared?
I know how smart you are!
Why do you do things
that cause you to have
to take make-up exams.
[KOBAYASHI]
Hm.
[HASHIBA]
Don't 'Hm' me!
They don't interest me.
I won't take them.
[HASHIBA gasps]
There's no way you're serious.
[KOBAYASHI]
I am serious.
[HASHIBA]
If you do the work now,
your life will be
easier down the road.
[KOBAYASHI]
I'm not too worried about it.
[HASHIBA] You're really
starting to make me mad.
[KOBAYASHI] It's not my
fault you worry so much.
I used to have a
friendship like yours.
[KOBAYASHI, HASHIBA]
Hm?
We only argued one time,
unlike you two.
[HASHIBA]
Uh. So, what happened?
Will you tell us more
about your friend?
Namikoshi.
Then he became...
the first Twenty Faces.
--[KOBAYASHI] Really?
--[HASHIBA gasps]
[AKECHI] I didn't have many
friends to hang out with.
To be honest, I didn't consider
anyone in my life a friend.
My intellect was
so high for a child
that the adults couldn't
even keep up with me.
So the other kids my age
didn't have a chance.
It isolated me.
[DELINQUENTS chuckle]
[DELINQUENT A]
Hey, math geek!
You're listening, right?
Did your mom hump a calculator?
[DELINQUENT C]
Everyone hates you!
[DELINQUENT B] Too scared to
speak up for yourself, huh?
[DELINQUENT C]
Don't you have anything to say?
[DELINQUENT A]
He's such a little wuss!
[DELINQUENTS groaning]
[AKECHI]
Here's your work.
The calculations you wrote
are pretty fascinating.
What are they for?
[AKECHI] For whatever reason,
he was the first person my age
I felt inclined to start
a conversation with.
Who are you?
[AKECHI]
Kogoro Akechi. What's your name?
Namikoshi.
Can you really
understand all my work?
[AKECHI]
More or less.
It's nice to meet you.
[AKECHI]
For the first time,
I experienced an intellect equal
to my own, and it was thrilling.
[AKECHI] I've never met
a junior high student
with a working knowledge
of Chaos Theory.
Could you show me some more?
Would you be interested
in working together?
[AKECHI] Altering humanity.
Do you think it's possible?
Well, don't they say that two
heads are better than one?
I guess so, but still.
This is gonna be tough,
even for two of us.
It's a lot of fun.
Don't you agree?
I'm enjoying it.
Yeah, me too.
[AKECHI]
We had more time and talent
than we knew
what to do with,
so we poured it all
into the formula.
Everything needed to be compiled
and encrypted inside a network.
I don't recall which one of us
first called it our brainchild.
[NAMIKOSHI] The results of
the calculations are arriving.
[AKECHI] Somehow you implicitly
led your own subjects
to help with calculations.
That's impressive.
I'm astonished by how close we
are to completing the formula.
You just passed
another benchmark.
I couldn't have done this alone.
But with your help,
I know we'll succeed.
Thank you so much.
My pleasure.
[AKECHI] Soon enough,
a new existence arose.
Through combined efforts,
we drew closer to our vision.
[NAMIKOSHI] A concept developed
from a simple formula,
becomes a legend that
spreads like a virus.
It grows into a masked
champion who destroys
whatever evil might
exist on this Earth.
A symbolic entity that was
derived from Dark Star.
A phenomenon in human form.
Its name...
...is Twenty Faces.
[AKECHI]
It should have ended there.
I had already started
trying to distance myself
from the project.
[KOBAYASHI]
Did something happen?
I realized that we had
made a deadly mistake.
[AKECHI]
But, Namikoshi...
[NAMIKOSHI]
The phenomenon will accelerate.
It starts as just
an underground myth,
but people will take
on the identity
in order to pass
anonymous judgment.
Fearless vigilantes capable
of committing impossible
crimes will be born.
No evil can escape
Twenty Faces.
[ALL grunting]
[groans]
[AKECHI]
Namikoshi! Stop!
Yes?
[AKECHI]
Did you start the reaction?
[NAMIKOSHI]
Yes.
What for?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm verifying the success of
our formula. It's perfection.
This is wrong!
[AKECHI]
The ideology had a deadly flaw.
If anyone truly knew the
past, present, and future,
and exacted their
own form of justice,
they were bound to be lost
in a cycle of vengeance.
[NAMIKOSHI]
I'm confused.
I don't understand why you're
saying things like that, Akechi.
I've already explained
my reasoning.
[NAMIKOSHI]
We can't stop now.
We're so close to everything
we've worked for!
[AKECHI gasps] A failure
is a failure. It's over.
[gasps]
[NAMIKOSHI] I disagree.
It isn't a failure.
[NAMIKOSHI]
I'll prove it to you. I swear.
[AKECHI] That was our
first and only argument.
[AKECHI]
And then...
[AKECHI panting]
[gasps]
A self-immolation
at Shinjuku Station.
It happened three years ago.
[AKECHI] After that day,
more of them popped up,
acting on misguided notions.
Vigilantes, each one unique.
Our original intentions had
been warped by Twenty Faces.
Selfish ambition often drove
them, evil begetting evil.
And I took it upon myself
to catch every Twenty Faces
that emerged, and crush them.
[AKECHI] I received my
title soon afterward.
Agency Detective. Kogoro Akechi.
So I guess, maybe,
that's what drives you?
Is that why you put
so much effort
into catching Twenty Faces?
To avenge your friend?
[AKECHI]
Namikoshi is dead.
There's nothing that
the living can do
for those who've passed away.
It won't change anything.
So, no.
At this point, I only crush
Twenty Faces for my own ego.
I'm not so different from
Kagami and Higashikoji.
Not true.
[AKECHI]
So I think you chose correctly.
[gasps]
Keep him from dying in
the first place, right?
[KOBAYASHI]
Uh?
[HASHIBA]
Uh. Right!
I was only asking a
hypothetical question.
[HASHIBA] That's not exactly
what we're talking about.
[KOBAYASHI]
It isn't?
Then you should tell
me what I'm missing.
[HASHIBA]
It's complicated.
I don't really know
how to explain.
[KOBAYASHI]
Why?
[HASHIBA] You don't
need to worry about it.
It's not a big deal.
You'll have to take the make-up
tests, so you need to....