DAMN IT.
[train horn blows]
PLEASE,
LET ME HELP YOU.
[train horn blows]
NARU...SE.
[gasps]
["Angel" by angela playing]
H-HARUTO.
[Aoi murmurs]
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
AOI. THANK GOD.
YOU HAD ME
WORRIED THERE.
OH, HEY, IBARA.
WHERE ARE WE?
[gasps] ARE YOU SAYING
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING?
[gasps]
DID I MAKE A MISTAKE?
PLEASE TELL ME
I DIDN'T SCREW
EVERYTHING UP AGAIN.
[crying]
I'M SO SORRY.
I SWEAR I DIDN'T
MEAN TO DO ANYTHING.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
I'M SUCH
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
LOSER.
[crying]
THAT IS
JUST NOT TRUE AT ALL.
WE WOULDN'T HAVE MADE IT
WITHOUT YOUR
HEROIC EFFORTS
BACK THERE.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD.
OH, DO YOU
MEAN THAT, IBARA?
SO WHAT ABOUT
OUR PLAN?
IS IT ALL GOING
THE WAY THAT WE
HOPED IT WOULD GO?
AS YOU CAN SEE RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE STILL WAITING
FOR THE TRAIN TO SHOW UP.
[gasps] THAT MEANS
OUR MISSION IS
NEARLY COMPLETE.
HOORAY!
YEAH, THE TRAIN WILL
DEFINITELY BE COMING.
HARUTO WILL MAKE SURE
IT GETS HERE. I KNOW IT.
HARUTO.
[crying]
I'M NEVER
GOING TO FORGET
THE WORDS
YOU SAID TO ME.
I'LL SAVE THE WORLD
WITH MY OWN HANDS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ONE OLD MAN
CAN BE EXPECTED TO DO
BY HIMSELF,
BUT I PROMISE
TO TRY MY BEST!
WHAT DO YOU
THINK IS TAKING
THE TRAIN SO LONG?
MISS AOI,
GOOD TO SEE YOU
ARE AWAKE.
AH! HI, NO-SENSE.
THANKS FOR PATROLLING
THE AREA, GUYS.
DID YOU SEE
ANYTHING UNUSUAL?
FOR THE TIME BEING,
EVERYTHING REMAINS
CALM AND SECURE.
THE FIRST DIVISION
MUST HAVE LOST
THEIR WILL TO FIGHT.
THEY'VE RESIGNED THEMSELVES
TO BEING SWALLOWED
BY THE WIND.
[glass shatters]
HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
THAT SOUNDED LIKE
SOME GLASS SHATTERING.
AOI, YOU STAY BACK HERE.
WHAT?! WAIT!
DON'T LEAVE ME!
SHIT.
THEY JUST KEEP
COMING BACK.
Ibara:
OZU SISTERS.
[chuckles]
DAMN IT.
WHEN WILL THEY GIVE UP?
WHAT NOW?
SIS, YOU SURE
THEY CAME HERE?
OH, THEY'RE HERE,
ALL RIGHT.
MY SENSES
ARE PICKING UP
REALLY STRONG SIGNALS
FROM THEM.
THEY'RE HEADED
THIS WAY!
THE HELL WITH IT
ALREADY!
AND THERE YOU GO.
I TOLD YOU THEY WERE
IN HERE, SHION.
YEAH, BUT WE CAN'T GET
ANYWHERE NEAR THEM, CAN WE?
KEEP THE TWO OF
THEM CORNERED.
DON'T LET THEM
GET ANY CLOSER
TO THE PLATFORM!
NO PROBLEM.
I'VE GOT PLENTY
OF AMMO.
IT'S ALREADY
PAST 5 P.M.
HOW LONG DO
THEY INTEND TO KEEP
US WORLD LEADERS
WAITING?
WHY HAVEN'T
WE RECONVENED?
ALL WE NEED
IS A CLEAR POSITION
FROM JAPAN
IN ORDER
FOR THE TALKS
TO MOVE FORWARD.
IBUSE, HAVE
A RESCUE CHOPPER
STANDING BY.
WHAT? BUT WE'RE
ON SECURITY DUTY, SIR.
OUR ORDERS
ARE TO STAY ON GUARD
UNTIL THE CONFERENCE
IS FINISHED UP TOMORROW.
I'M THROUGH WITH
PLAYING SECURITY GUARD.
MY MISSION IS
TO SAVE LIVES.
WE'LL LEAVE FOR
THE OLD CAPITAL TONIGHT.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT ANYONE SAYS.
OH, WELL, THEN.
IT'LL ONLY COST ME
MY SALARY. HEH.
SHION, KANON,
LISTEN TO ME!
SURRENDER YOURSELVES
PEACEFULLY!
I KNOW YOU'RE
BOTH BADLY HURT!
IF YOU
COME ON OUT NOW,
WE'LL TEND
TO YOUR WOUNDS.
SURRENDER?
[both laughing]
DO WE
REALLY LOOK LIKE
THE KIND OF GIRLS
WHO'D SURRENDER
TO ANYONE?
BESIDES, WHAT ARE
WE SUPPOSED TO DO
AFTER YOU
HELP US OUT,
JOIN TOGETHER
AS A TEAM SAVING
HUMAN LIVES?
THAT'S WHERE
WE DIFFER, NARUSE.
I'D RATHER DIE
THAN BLINDLY FOLLOW
ANY ORDERS
THE SCHOOL GAVE US!
ARE YOU OK, SIS?
CLASS PRESIDENT,
IBARA NARUSE,
YOU'RE ABLE TO SAY
SHIT LIKE THAT
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"DON'T KNOW ANYTHING"?
ABOUT WHAT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT
SAVING LIVES!
YOU SERIOUSLY
BELIEVE THE COPPELION
WERE CREATED
FOR HUMANITARIAN
AND RESCUE MISSIONS?
IT'S ALL BULLSHIT.
THE ADULTS ARE
MANIPULATING YOU
AS IF YOU WERE
SOME KIND OF PUPPET.
I--I DON'T
UNDERSTAND
ANY OF THIS.
[laughs]
YOU NEVER DO.
THAT'S YOUR EXCUSE
FOR RUNNING AWAY FROM
EVERY PREDICAMENT.
THERE ISN'T ONE
DIFFICULT LIFE ISSUE
YOU'VE EVER
UNDERSTOOD.
[chuckles]
WELL, YOU JUST
GO RIGHT ON AHEAD
FOLLOWING THOSE RULES,
MISS CLASS PRESIDENT...
IF, THAT IS,
YOU FIND A WAY
TO DEFEAT US FIRST.
BUT, SIS,
IF YOU USE ANY MORE
OF YOUR POWER,
YOUR BODY WILL--
WHO GIVES A SHIT?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE
HAVE A FUTURE, DO WE?
[footsteps]
DAMN IT.
Husband:
THE FIRST
DIVISION.
HEH.
YOU WANT
TO GET TO IT, THEN...
OUR FINAL BATTLE?
[train clacking]
THAT SOUND.
[train horn blows]
IT'S THE TRAIN!
THE TRAIN'S HERE.
IF WE DON'T GET
TO IT QUICKLY,
WE'LL BE LEFT BEHIND.
WE CAN'T GET AWAY
JUST YET,
BECAUSE
THE OZU SISTERS
WILL KNOW OUR PLANS.
IF WE DON'T
STOP THEM SOMEHOW,
THEY'LL DESTROY
THE TRAIN.
BUT HOW?
THERE'S JUST
TOO MANY OF THEM.
PLEASE TELL ME
YOU HAVE A PLAN.
ACTUALLY, I DO.
WE'LL USE
OUR FINAL TRAP
THAT HARUTO WAS ABLE
TO SET UP EARLIER.
[gasps]
IF YOU GUYS
DON'T HURRY UP,
I'M GETTING ON FIRST!
OK, WE'RE
GETTING CLOSE
TO THE STATION,
SO YOU CAN
SLOW HER DOWN,
KUROBE.
HEY, ARE YOU
LISTENING?
[gasping]
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU LOOK PALE.
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY.
MAYBE THE AETHER
IS WEARING OFF.
THE GIRL DID
SAY IT'S ONLY SUPPOSED
TO LAST 10 MINUTES.
OH, GOD. THEN YOU
NEED TO GO AND GET
INSIDE THE SHELTER RIGHT NOW,
BEFORE THE AETHER
WEARS OFF.
I'LL DO THE DRIVING.
OK.
THANKS, GOJIRO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
IT'S TOO MUCH!
IT HURTS!
HANG IN THERE.
KEEP BREATHING
STEADILY.
I CAN'T!
[screams]
[radio whines]
GRANNY AYAME.
IT'S POSSIBLE
THE BABY'S CAUGHT
ON SOMETHING
INSIDE THE WOMB.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
CAUGHT ON WHAT?
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU MENTIONED EARLIER
THAT SHE'S BEEN ANEMIC
SINCE HER
FIRST TRIMESTER.
IS THAT CORRECT?
YES.
[groans]
HURRY UP, YOU GUYS!
WE GOTTA GET GOING!
THE TRAIN IS ALMOST
AT THE PLATFORM!
HEY!
THE MAINTENANCE TEAM
IS ARRIVING NOW!
WHERE'D
EVERYBODY GO?!
WE HAVE TO GET
OUT OF HERE!
DAMN MONSTER.
Ibara: DON'T SHOOT.
GET TO THE PLATFORM.
[gasping]
HURRY. THE TRAIN'S
GONNA LEAVE.
JUST GET GOING,
AND DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME. [gasps]
YOU GUYS ARE
GETTING ON A TRAIN?
WELL,
I'LL MAKE SURE THEN
THAT TRAIN
TAKES YOU TO HELL!
OW. OW. OW.
[laughs]
DAMN YOU,
CLASS PRESIDENT.
I'LL TRASH
THAT TRAIN.
THE ONLY THING
THAT'S GETTING TRASHED
IS THAT CEILING.
WHAT? A BOMB?
GOD DAMN YOU,
NARUSE!
SHION.
Aoi: IBARA!
HURRY!
EVERYONE ELSE
IS ON BOARD NOW.
COME ON!
WE'VE GOTTA
GET GOING!
I CAN'T SLOW DOWN
THE TRAIN ANY MORE.
I HAVE TO PICK UP THE PACE
IN ORDER TO BREAK
THROUGH THE ZONE.
LET'S GO!
[panting]
[crash]
HUH?
Ibara: SHION.
[giggles]
YOU KNOW WHAT
I THINK WOULD BE FUN?
SMASHING EVERYTHING.
STOP THIS RECKLESSNESS.
PUT THAT THING DOWN.
EH, I'M LOSING
MY STRENGTH.
HANG ON!
[gasps]
SH-SHION.
Aoi: YOU GOTTA GET
ON THIS TRAIN RIGHT NOW!
PLEASE, HURRY!
[chuckles]
WAY TO GO, FOREMAN.
YES!
NOW THAT'S WHAT
I CALL TEAMWORK!
Aoi: IBARA, ARE YOU OK?
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
THE FIRST DIVISION?
LET'S ALL GET
OUT OF THIS ALIVE.
COME GET
ON THE TRAIN, GUYS!
Kurobe: JESUS.
SHE BROUGHT
THE WHOLE GANG
ALONG WITH US.
Solider:
YOU'RE AN ANGEL.
Aoi: MR. GENNAI!
THIS IS SOME KIND
OF JOKE, RIGHT?
WHY'D THIS
HAVE TO HAPPEN?
DON'T DIE,
MR. GENNAI.
OH, YOU SWEET
LITTLE GIRL.
THIS ISN'T
YOUR FAULT.
I WISH HE HAD TAKEN
MY AETHER SHOT.
HOW BAD OFF IS HE NOW?
CAN WE SAVE HIM?
HOW MUCH TIME
DOES THE POOR GUY
HAVE LEFT TO LIVE?
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
Gojiro, over P.A.:
OK, EVERYONE, LISTEN UP.
THE TRAIN WILL BE
AT THE ZONE SOON,
SO HANG TIGHT, BECAUSE YOU
ALL KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS.
THIS IS WHEN THINGS
GET SERIOUS.
THE HEAVY FOG FROM THE ZONE
IS FIVE KILOMETERS
AHEAD OF US.
ALL OUR HARD WORK
COMES DOWN TO THIS MOMENT.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT
THROUGH THAT FOG!
EVERYONE GO GET
INSIDE THE SHELTER.
I'LL TAKE OVER
THE DRIVING
FROM HERE ON OUT.
OK. YOU GOT IT.
WHERE'S HARUTO?
I NEED HIM UP HERE.
THIS IS NO TIME
FOR HIM TO BE
SITTING AROUND
OR SLACKING OFF
AND WASTING OUR--
HMM?
I'M SORRY, KID,
BUT HE'S, UH...
NO! YOU'RE LYING!
LET ME GO! HARUTO!
HE CAN'T BE DEAD!
HE JUST CAN'T!
HARUTO!
Ayame: ALL RIGHT,
LISTEN CAREFULLY.
THE WAY
IT LOOKS NOW,
THE BABY IS
BEING OBSTRUCTED.
IF WE MAKE A MISTAKE,
BOTH MOTHER AND CHILD
COULD DIE.
Taeko: BUT WHY IS
THIS HAPPENING?
YOU'RE GONNA FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH.
RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE
TO MAKE AN IMPORTANT
LIFE-OR-DEATH DECISION,
DO WE SAVE THE MOTHER
OR THE CHILD?
HARUTO,
YOU LIED TO ME.
YOU PROMISED
WE'D SEE EACH OTHER
AGAIN SOON.
[sobbing]
IBARA, PLEASE
PULL YOURSELF
TOGETHER.
THIS IS NO TIME
FOR TEARS.
THE ZONE
HAS ALMOST
CAUGHT UP TO US.
Gojiro: HEY, ARE YOU
PAYING ATTENTION, COPPELION!
WE'RE ALMOST
AT THE FIVE-KILOMETER POINT!
COME TAKE OVER!
YOU'VE GOTTA
SNAP OUT OF IT
RIGHT NOW, IBARA!
IT WAS YOUR STRENGTH
AND DEDICATION
TO THE MISSION
THAT BROUGHT US
THIS FAR.
IF IT HADN'T BEEN
FOR YOUR LEADERSHIP,
WE WOULD HAVE
ALL GIVEN UP
A LONG TIME AGO.
THIS IS A SAD WORLD,
AND PEOPLE
LOSE SIGHT
OF WHY THEY
SHOULD GO ON LIVING.
EVERYONE'S FELT
THAT WAY AT ONE TIME
OR ANOTHER,
THAT THERE'S
NO FUTURE,
THAT IT'D BE EASIER
IF WE JUST--
I'VE FELT
THE SAME WAY, TOO,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT
CHANGED ALL THAT?
YOUR SMILE.
WHEN WE ALL SEE
YOUR BEAUTIFUL SMILE,
IT GIVES US THE COURAGE
TO MOVE FORWARD
AND KEEP LIVING.
I'M TELLING YOU
THE TRUTH HERE, IBARA.
YOUR SMILE HAS GOT
THAT KIND OF POWER.
Haruto: NARUSE.
DON'T LOOK SO SAD.
HARUTO?
[crying]
I'M SORRY, AOI.
[gasps]
LET'S DO THIS.
LET'S BUST
THROUGH THAT ZONE.
Gojiro:
HURRY UP, COPPELION!
I'LL TAKE OVER FROM HERE.
HUH?
YOU NEED TO GET
BACK TO THE SHELTER.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT,
GRANNY AYAME?
WHY DO YOU WANT ME
TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
MOTHER AND CHILD?
THE UMBILICAL CORD
HAS WRAPPED AROUND
THE BABY'S NECK.
THERE IS DEFINITELY
A POSSIBILITY
OF SUFFOCATION.
SOMETIMES
THESE THINGS
WILL HAPPEN,
BUT YOU CAN
TAKE CARE OF IT.
THE THING IS,
IN THIS CASE,
YOU'LL PROBABLY
HAVE TO PERFORM
A CAESARIAN SECTION.
IT'S THE BEST WAY
FOR US TO ENSURE
THE BABY'S SAFETY.
CAESARIAN SECTION?
BUT HERE'S
THE PROBLEM.
SINCE YOU HAVE
NO EXPERIENCE
PERFORMING A SURGERY
SUCH AS THIS,
THERE'S NO WAY
TO KNOW FOR SURE
THAT THE MOTHER
WILL SURVIVE,
WHICH IS WHY
I WAS JUST SAYING
THAT--THAT, WELL...
THAT YOU
WANT ME TO CHOOSE
WHICH ONE
I WANT TO SAVE.
[beeping]
HEY.
LOOK AT
THE COUNTER
READINGS.
THE NUMBERS
ARE RISING UP
AND GOING FASTER
AND FASTER.
889. 895.
EXCEEDING
MAXIMUM LIMIT!
A WHITE CLOUD
IS DIRECTLY AHEAD.
IS THAT IT?
IS THAT THE ZONE BARRIER
WE HAVE TO GET PAST?
IT'S SO CRAMPED IN HERE!
[moos]
[over P.A.]
THIS IS IBARA.
WE'RE ABOUT TO PASS
DIRECTLY THROUGH
THE ZONE FOG.
THOSE OF YOU
IN THE SHELTER
NEED TO STAY PUT.
DO NOT OPEN THE DOORS
UNTIL I GIVE
THE ALL CLEAR.
WHATEVER'S GONNA HAPPEN,
IT'LL BE OVER QUICKLY.
REMEMBER,
WE RISKED OUR LIVES
FIGHTING FOR THIS ONE,
SINGLE MOMENT.
WE'RE GOING
TO MAKE IT OUT ALIVE!
THE STRENGTH
OF OUR CONVICTIONS
HAS BROUGHT US
THIS FAR.
WE'LL GO ON
WITHOUT ANY DOUBT
OR HESITATION.
HOLD STRONG, AND BELIEVE
IN THE POWER OF LIFE.
Ibuki:
TAEKO, LISTEN TO ME.
I WAS PREPARED
FOR THE WORST
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING, OK?
I'LL RISK DEATH.
IT'S OK.
YOU JUST HAVE
TO SAVE THIS CHILD.
IT WON'T BE LIKE THAT,
MISS IBUKI.
DON'T WORRY.
I STUDIED HARD
IN SURGERY
SO THAT I WOULD BE READY
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
I'M GOING
TO PROVE IT TO YOU.
I'LL SAVE BOTH YOU
AND YOUR BABY.
ARE YOU READY
TO DO THIS, AOI?
YEAH!
LET'S BREAK THROUGH IT!
[gasps]
IT'S SO WHITE,
A WHITE WORLD.
Ibara: MAKE IT THROUGH.
MAKE IT THROUGH.
MAKE IT THROUGH!
[train horn honks]
LOOK AT THAT,
A FLOCK OF BIRDS.
WAY TO GO, IBARA!
YOU DID IT!
WE MADE IT
THROUGH THE FOG!
SHELTER,
THIS IS IBARA.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
SHELTER,
PLEASE RESPOND.
Kurobe: WE HEAR YOU
LOUD AND CLEAR.
[cheering]
CAN YOU HEAR US?
WE'VE ALREADY
STARTED
THE CELEBRATION
BACK HERE.
[overlapping chatter,
laughter]
OK, THE READINGS
HAVE FALLEN WITHIN
SAFE LEVELS.
SO HERE'S
SOME GOOD NEWS.
IT'S SAFE FOR
EVERYONE TO COME
BACK OUT NOW.
YOU DID IT,
MISS CLASS PRESIDENT!
[laughs]
[cheering]
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED!
WE SHOWED THEM.
[laughs]
OUCH! YOU'RE
CRUSHING MY BONES!
OOPS. I'M SORRY.
I FORGOT ABOUT
YOUR ARM.
Soldiers: ONE!
[Aoi squealing, laughing]
IS EVERYONE
DOING OK?
Gojiro: YEAH,
THANKS TO YOU,
CLASS PRESIDENT.
2!
WE MADE IT
RIGHT PAST THAT
THICK ZONE FOG.
THE PLAN WAS
A HUGE SUCCESS.
PUT ME DOWN!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU DON'T SEEM
VERY HAPPY
ABOUT THIS.
WE ALL OWE HIM
OUR THANKS AS WELL,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
I FOUND THIS BOMB
THAT HARUTO HAD LEFT BEHIND.
I'M SURE HE WOULD HAVE
WANTED YOU TO HAVE IT.
IBUKI, IT'S ME.
PLEASE ANSWER.
THE FATHER OF YOUR BABY.
[gasps]
HAS IT BEEN BORN?
WHAT'S HAPPENING
IN THERE? HEY!
DID I HEAR THAT RIGHT?
YOU'RE THE BABY'S FATHER?!
SO IT WAS YOU!
YOU'RE THE BASTARD
WHO LAID HANDS
ON MY DAUGHTER!
YOU PIECE OF SHIT!
WHAT THE HELL'S
WRONG WITH YOU?!
WHAT WERE
YOU THINKING?!
CALM DOWN
FOR A MINUTE, GOJIRO.
HOLD ON.
[static crackling]
YOU MESSED UP
BIG TIME.
COME ON.
THIS ISN'T TIME
FOR FIGHTING.
Ayame, crackling:
TAEKO, WHAT'S HAPPENING
OVER THERE?
THIS IS GRANNY AYAME
IN NAGOYA.
WILL SOMEBODY ANSWER?
HELLO?
GRANNY AYAME,
IS THAT REALLY YOU?
HEY, GRANNY,
CAN YOU TELL ME
HOW MISS IBUKI'S
CHILDBIRTH
IS GOING?
WHO AM I SPEAKING WITH NOW?
JUST FORGET ABOUT IT.
PUT TAEKO BACK
ON THE RADIO RIGHT AWAY.
WE'RE TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
WHETHER OR NOT
TO GO AHEAD WITH
THE CAESARIAN SECTION.
IF WE
DON'T ACT QUICKLY,
THE BABY
WILL CHOKE TO DEATH.
DID SHE SAY,
"CAESARIAN SECTION"?
ARE IBUKI AND THE BABY
ALL RIGHT?
EVERYONE,
THIS IS TAEKO.
PLEASE BE QUIET.
I CAN'T STEP AWAY,
BECAUSE I'M
OPERATING.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY NOW.
I PROMISE TO SAVE
BOTH MISS IBUKI
AND HER BABY.
PLEASE
JUST GET THIS TRAIN
TO A SAFE LOCATION.
GRANNY AYAME,
CONTINUE
GUIDING ME THROUGH
THIS PROCEDURE.
[grunts]
OK, TAIKO!
DOWNTOWN AREA,
HERE WE COME!
YOU ALIVE? SHION?
IS THAT YOU, SIS?
I DON'T GET IT.
I WAS CRUSHED
UNDER A MASSIVE
CHUNK OF RUBBLE.
ANY ORDINARY
HUMAN BEING
WOULD BE DEAD
BY NOW, RIGHT?
WHY? TELL ME WHY
AM I STILL ALIVE.
IT REALLY HURTS,
SIS.
MY WHOLE BODY
HURTS SO BADLY,
IT'S KILLING ME.
MAKE IT STOP!
I JUST WANNA DIE
LIKE A REGULAR PERSON!
[sobbing]
KILL ME.
PUT ME OUT
OF MY MISERY, SIS.
PLEASE,
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
LIKE THIS ANYMORE.
THERE'S NO HOPE,
ANYWAY.
WE'RE JUST GONNA
DROP DEAD SOMEDAY
WITHOUT ANY WARNING.
WHY CAN'T WE JUST
END IT RIGHT HERE
AND NOW?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE LUCKY THAT YOU
STILL HAVE THE ABILITY
TO FEEL PAIN.
LOOK AT ME.
I CAN'T FEEL ANYTHING.
YOU SEE, MY BODY
IS CONSTANTLY TINGLING
FROM ALL
THIS ELECTRICITY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT PAIN FEELS LIKE ANYMORE.
THAT'S SO SAD.
I'M A DOLL,
AND THAT'S ALL
I'LL EVER BE.
I WAS NEVER HUMAN
TO BEGIN WITH.
I'M NOTHING
BUT AN ANIMATED DOLL.
IS THAT IT,
MR. GENNAI?
YES, IT IS.
IN A LITTLE WHILE NOW,
THE SKYSCRAPERS
WILL BE PAINTED RED
WITH THE LIGHT
OF THE SETTING SUN.
I HOPE I GET TO SEE IT
WITH ALL OF YOU.
YOU WILL, I PROMISE.
[heavy thudding]
HUH?
[gasps]
NO WAY.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Ibara: BEYOND THE MEMORIES...
HARUTO'S MEMENTO...
TEARS...
FRIENDS...
THE SKYSCRAPERS...
SORA AND RIKU...
DAYBREAK...
GOODBYES...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
ANGEL.