SHIT.
IT'S THE IRON SPIDER.
IRON SPIDER?
THE FIRST DIVISION'S
SECRET WEAPON.
[whimpers]
Husband: THAT'S
THE FLAMETHROWER!
Ibara: RUN!
IT'S GONNA FIRE!
["Angel" by angela playing]
THEY WON'T STOP
UNTIL THEY'VE
DESTROYED THE CITY.
WHY DO YOU HUMANS
TRY TO HURT EACH OTHER?
IF YOU WERE
ALL MADE EQUAL,
HOW COME YOU
CAN'T PEACEFULLY
EXIST TOGETHER?
[gasps]
MISS AOI.
[sighs]
OH, NO! MY SWEATER
GOT CAUGHT
IN THIS THING!
[screaming]
OH. [chuckles]
AWESOME LANDING.
JUST LIKE
I PLANNED IT.
[clanking]
IT'S HEADED
THIS WAY!
STEP ON IT,
HARUTO!
[yells]
WE'VE GOTTA STOP IT
BEFORE IT KILLS US.
THE HATCH
UNDER ITS BELLY!
IT'S ITS WEAK POINT!
THAT'S WHERE
THE MOTOR IS.
THERE IT IS.
TAKE THIS!
[pilots groan]
I'VE LOST CONTROL!
Ibara: DAMN IT.
THE HATCH DIDN'T
EVEN BUDGE.
UH-OH. I THINK THAT'S
THE POLICE STATION.
IS THAT WHERE THE GUY
IN THE WHITE COAT
IS LOCKED UP?
THANKS FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE.
WE'RE
IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
GO FOR ITS SWITCH.
HMM?
THERE'S A MANUAL SWITCH
AT THE END OF THE ABDOMEN
THAT OPENS UP THE HATCH.
HOW ARE
WE SUPPOSED TO CLIMB
ALL THE WAY UP THERE?
WHOOP!
Aoi: EH. OH, NO.
IT'S
THE OZU SISTERS!
IBARA, LOOK.
THEY'RE
GAINING ON US!
WE'VE GOTTA
GO FASTER!
WE'RE JUST
BARELY OUTRUNNING
THE IRON SPIDER.
[gasps]
WE'LL USE THIS WIRE GUN
TO GET AT THE SWITCH.
I THINK
I CAN HIT THE SPIKE
COMING OUT
OF THE IRON SPIDER'S
ABDOMEN.
WE'LL CLIMB OUR WAY UP.
WHAT IF
THE OZU SISTERS
ATTACK THE WIRE
ONCE IT'S SET UP?
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO KEEP THEM OCCUPIED THEN.
THAT MEANS
I CAN'T GO UP THERE.
ONE OF YOU NEEDS
TO PUSH THE SWITCH.
[whimpers]
I'LL DO IT, IBARA.
[gulps]
I NEED TO HELP.
I DON'T WANT
TO BACK DOWN.
I'LL DO
EVERYTHING I CAN
TO HELP MAKE A BETTER
AND BRIGHTER WORLD.
[gasps]
MM.
THERE. GOT IT.
[screams]
I SEE SOMETHING.
THAT MUST
BE THE SWITCH
TO THE HATCH.
I'M READY!
DO IT NOW,
SIS!
[thunder crashes]
[yells]
WHY IS SHE SHOCKING SHION?
[grunts]
ELECTRIC ATTACK!
NOW HOLD IT
RIGHT THERE, SHION.
HUH?
[yells]
[grunts]
OK, I MADE IT.
NOW I JUST
PUSH THIS BUTTON,
AND THE HATCH WILL OPEN.
[screams]
I BROKE MY FINGER!
[yells]
WHAT THE HECK?!
STUPID REINFORCED GLASS!
[Aoi yells]
THAT SNEAKY
LITTLE PAIN IN THE ASS.
OH, NO.
I'M IN BIG TROUBLE!
[screams]
SHIT. I'M STARTING
TO RUN REALLY LOW
ON POWER.
DAMN YOU, HARUTO!
Shion: GOD,
YOU'RE SO STUBBORN.
WHY ARE YOU
TRYING SO HARD
TO HELP HUMANS?
THEY'RE WORTHLESS!
[bone cracks]
[screams]
[gasps]
SIS, SHOW THIS BITCH
HOW AOI FUKASAKU
MEETS HER END.
YOU GOT IT, SHION.
[screams]
AOI!
SHE ABSORBED
MY ELECTRICITY?
[steam whistling]
HEY, COME BACK HERE!
THAT'S ENOUGH.
DIE ALREADY!
[thunder crashes]
SHE'S FLOATING?
Commander:
IS SHE SOME KIND
OF MONSTER?
TAKE THIS.
HERE YOU GO.
[groans]
WHAT HAPPENED?
SHE DID IT.
NARUSE DESTROYED
THE IRON SPIDER.
Haruto: AOI FUKASAKU,
WHAT ARE YOU?
DID YOU KNOW,
NARUSE?
KNOW WHAT?
SCIENCE HAS
TWO SIDES,
POSITIVE
AND NEGATIVE.
POSITIVE AND NEGATIVE.
NARUSE.
POSITIVE--[gasps]
HEY, SNAP OUT OF IT.
WHERE'S AOI? [winces]
SHE'S OVER THERE.
DON'T WORRY.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT POWER WAS
THAT AOI USED
TO SAVE ME, HARUTO?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
HEY...
BAD NEWS.
WE COULDN'T
FIND THEIR BODIES
ANYWHERE,
NOT THE OZU SISTERS
OR THE WHITE COAT.
OUR PLAN
WILL BE EXPOSED
IF WE DON'T DRAW
THEIR ATTENTION BACK TO US.
THAT'S TRUE,
BUT WE HAVE
A BIGGER PROBLEM
TO DEAL WITH.
IT'S ALREADY
1600 HOURS?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE TIME?
YOU WERE OUT
FOR A WHILE,
SO IT FEELS
EARLIER TO YOU.
BUT WHERE'S THE TRAIN?
IT'S NOT HERE YET?!
NO. I HAVEN'T SEEN
A TRACE OF IT.
THE MAINTENANCE TEAM
MIGHT HAVE RUN INTO
SOME TROUBLE.
THEN I'M GONNA GO
AND HELP THEM
GET OUT OF IT.
[winces]
Husband: YOU CAN'T.
NOT WITH THAT ARM.
NO, I'M FINE, OK?
THIS IS NOTHING.
A TERRIBLE LIAR
AS ALWAYS.
STAY HERE, AND REST.
I'LL GO CHECK OUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
HARUTO.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER,
NARUSE.
WAIT.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA
BE BACK SOON, RIGHT?
SCIENCE WILL ALWAYS
HAVE TWO SIDES TO IT.
YOU'RE DEFINITELY
ON THE POSITIVE SIDE,
NARUSE.
DON'T LOOK SO SAD.
HARUTO.
Gennai:
WE DID IT!
THE ARMORED TRAIN
IS COMPLETE.
IT'S AMAZING
YOU DID THIS REBUILD
IN JUST HALF A DAY.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU GUYS
ON THE DIVERSION TEAM
DOING?
WE HAD
SOME SETBACKS.
BUT WHATEVER.
WE DON'T HAVE
MUCH TIME LEFT.
HOW'S MISS IBUKI
HOLDING UP
BACK THERE?
Kurobe: I HAVEN'T BEEN
INSIDE THE SHELTER,
SO I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY.
ALL WE CAN DO IS PRAY
FOR A SAFE DELIVERY.
THE TRAIN'S READY,
BUT THERE WAS A PROBLEM
AT THE TRANSFORMER
SUBSTATION,
SO GOJIRO
WENT TO FIX IT.
IF WITHIN
THE NEXT 40 MINUTES,
WE DON'T GET
THAT TRAIN STARTED,
THEN YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
YOU'RE ALL GONNA DIE.
WHAT?!
I KNEW SENDING GOJIRO
OUT THERE ON THIS JOB
WAS A MISTAKE.
HMM. THE GUY SAID
HE COULD FIX IT
BECAUSE HE USED TO WORK
FOR THE POWER COMPANY.
I'M GOING
TO THE SUBSTATION.
[thunder crashing]
Haruto:
WE COPPELION EXIST
BECAUSE OF
HUMAN MISTAKES,
SO WHY AM I TRYING
TO SAVE THEM?
Ibara: HARUTO, YOU
STILL WANT TO BELIEVE
IN HUMANS, DON'T YOU?
DAMN IT. WHY?
WHY ISN'T IT
GETTING ANY POWER?
I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME
WITH NO HELP.
IBUKI.
OH, IBUKI.
I'M SORRY
YOUR DAD CAN'T DO
ANY MORE FOR YOU.
[footstep]
HUH?
YOU CAN STILL DO IT.
HOW ABOUT
YOU LET ME HELP YOU?
I FIGURED IT OUT.
YOU WORKED
AT THAT COMPANY,
DIDN'T YOU?
[gasps]
DAMN IT.
THAT KUROBE'S
A BLABBERMOUTH.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN HIDING IT NOW.
IF WE DON'T HURRY,
THE WIND'LL
SWALLOW US UP.
LET'S SPLIT UP
AND TRY TO FIND
THE BREAK.
HMM.
Gojiro:
IN THOSE DAYS,
I OFTEN FELT
SO POWERLESS.
THE COUNTRY
SPENT HUGE AMOUNTS
OF MONEY EVERY YEAR,
BUT MOST OF THE FUNDING
THAT SHOULD HAVE GONE
TO SAFETY MEASURES
WAS CUT.
IN THE END,
FACILITY MANAGEMENT
WAS REASSIGNED
ELSEWHERE.
COMPANY EMPLOYEES
STARTED LEAVING
NOW-DANGEROUS
WORKPLACES.
[grunts]
I BEGAN TO THINK...
[crackling]
THIS IS JUST
HOW THE COUNTRY WORKS.
THE WHEELS FELL OFF
A LONG TIME AGO.
EVERYONE ACTED
LIKE NOTHING WAS WRONG.
THEY KEPT THEIR HEADS
BURIED IN THE SAND.
THAT ACCIDENT
WAS THE PRICE
WE ULTIMATELY PAID.
IT IS TRUE I WAS A COG
IN THAT BIG MACHINE.
IT COST MONEY TO DO
REGULAR INSPECTIONS.
THAT'S WHY I FOLLOWED
COMPANY ORDERS
AND CUT BACK ON
HOW MANY WE PERFORMED.
OVER HERE.
BECAUSE OF WHAT I DID,
MILLIONS HAD TO SUFFER.
Haruto: BUT YOU STAYED
UNTIL THE VERY END,
DIDN'T YOU?
THE ONLY ONE LEFT
IN THAT TREACHEROUS
WORKPLACE.
WHEN THE WHEELS FALL OFF,
WE JUST HAVE TO FIX 'EM.
AH, THE POWER'S WORKING.
WAY TO GO, GUYS.
[boom]
EH?
WHAT IN THE HELL
CAUSED THAT SOUND?
OH, NO.
THE POWER'S FAILING.
DO YOU THINK THAT SOUND
COULD HAVE BEEN...
Both:
AN ELECTRICAL POLE FALLING!
[panting]
HARUTO,
WHY DO YOU
HELP US HUMANS?
WE CREATED
THIS ROTTEN MESS,
AND WE'LL MAKE
THE SAME KIND OF MISTAKES
ALL OVER AGAIN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY YOU NEED
TO BE THE ONE
TO HELP THEM.
NO MATTER
HOW DANGEROUS
THE SITUATION IS,
YOU FACED THE PROBLEM
WITHOUT RUNNING AWAY.
AS LONG AS THERE ARE
STILL BRAVE PEOPLE
LIKE YOU,
ACCIDENTS
CAN BE AVOIDED.
SO YOU SEE,
THIS TIME, MR. GOJIRO,
I WANT YOU
TO SAVE MANKIND.
CAN YOU FIX IT, GENNAI?
[gunshots]
HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT SOUNDED
LIKE GUNSHOTS.
PLEASE HANG IN THERE,
HARUTO! DON'T DIE!
TOO BAD.
HE WAS SO CLOSE.
WHAT EXACTLY IS IT
THAT YOU WANT
FROM ALL THIS?
WHAT'S WORTH IT?
I DEVOTED MYSELF
TO THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF SERVING SOCIETY
AND THE PEOPLE.
TO GIVE OUR LIVES
TO PROTECT THIS COUNTRY,
THAT'S THE PLEDGE
MY MEN AND I MADE
BACK THEN.
I WONDER WHY
THEY'RE GIVING US
THESE MASKS.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
AN EARTHQUAKE
RESCUE.
THAT DAY, WE HEADED OUT
TO RESCUE
THE CITY'S CITIZENS.
LISTEN UP!
OUR MISSION IS
TO PROTECT THIS LAND
AND THE PEOPLE
AT ALL COSTS.
IS THAT CLEAR?
[soldiers yell]
I WENT
LOOKING AROUND TO FIND
THE THEN
MINISTER OF DEFENSE.
HE WAS A LONGTIME
FRIEND OF MINE,
DEFENSE MINISTER
NATSUME.
YOU KNOW HIM
AS THE CURRENT
PRIME MINISTER.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
HOW CAN SOMEONE FORSAKE
ALL OUR CITIZENS?
[gasps]
KUNIKIDA.
WE'RE BEING
LEFT IN THE DARK.
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?
I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA.
ALL I KNOW
IS OUR PRIORITY
IS PROTECTING
THE PRIME MINISTER.
UNDERSTOOD.
LEAVE THIS AREA TO US.
LOOK AFTER THE COUNTRY,
NATSUME.
MM.
Kunikida: BY THE TIME
I REALIZED THE TRUTH,
IT WAS ALREADY TOO LATE.
THE GOVERNMENT
ABANDONED THE CITIZENS
AND RAN AWAY
TO SAVE THEIR OWN NECKS.
IT'S ALWAYS THE WEAK
AND THE BRAVE
WHO ARE THE ONES WHO GET
LEFT BEHIND IN HELL.
WE DON'T NEED
A FUTURE THAT DEMANDS
SUCH A HIGH COST.
THEN WHY DIDN'T
YOU TAKE ANY ACTION
AT ALL UNTIL NOW?
WHAT?
ALL THIS TIME,
LIKE A GHOST,
YOU SAT AND WATCHED
WHAT WAS HAPPENING
TO THIS WORLD.
YOUR MOTIVATIONS
WERE THE SAME AS MINE.
YOU SEE, I KNOW YOU HAVE
A LEVEL OF BELIEF
IN HUMANITY,
AND NOW YOU WANT TO SEE
JUST HOW FAR IT CAN GO.
THOSE GIRLS LANDED
IN A DARK WORLD,
AND NOW THEY'RE
TRYING TO LIGHT
THE WAY FOR MANKIND.
YOU WANT THEM TO SUCCEED,
TO COMPLETE THEIR JOURNEY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT I WANT.
I HAVE COMRADES WHO
SHARE MY MISSION.
THERE'S
NO TURNING BACK.
I MUST CONTINUE.
DON'T DO IT!
[gunfire]
[gasps]
HEH. SORRY I'M
A LITTLE LATE, GUYS.
RETREAT.
[groans]
[laughs]
Haruto: DON'T SHOOT.
[carrier retreats]
THAT MAN IS STILL HUMAN.
PLEASE LET HIM GO.
YOU AREN'T SERIOUS.
AFTER EVERYTHING
THE BASTARD'S DONE TO YOU?
SHIT!
FINE, THEN.
YOU GUYS HURRY,
AND GET ON THE TRAIN.
WHAT, ARE YOU
NOT COMING
WITH US?
THERE'S A PROBLEM
WITH THE POWER LINE
NEAR THE SOUTH EXIT
THAT NEEDS TO BE FIXED.
GENNAI IS REPAIRING
THE POLE AS WE SPEAK.
THAT WON'T WORK.
WE'RE GOING TO
RUN OUT OF TIME.
IT'LL BE FINE.
I PROMISE.
IN CASE THERE'S
A MAJOR ISSUE,
WE MIGHT HAVE TO STAY
A LITTLE LONGER
TO BE SURE EVERYTHING
WORKS AS WE NEED IT TO.
IF SO, GO ON WITHOUT US.
HMM.
I'M NOT SHAKING
YOUR HAND NOW.
YOU'LL HAVE
TO COME BACK
FOR THAT.
HMM. YEAH, I HEAR YOU.
YOU'RE A GOOD MAN,
YOU KNOW.
DIDN'T NARUSE
GIVE YOU THE AETHER?
WELL, WE GAVE IT ALL
TO IBUKI
'CAUSE SHE NEEDED IT.
AS LONG AS THE BIRTH
GOES SAFELY FOR THEM,
THEN IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
TO THE REST OF US.
SORRY. I'M AFRAID
THIS IS ALL I HAVE.
HMM.
THANKS A BUNCH, KID.
I APPRECIATE YOUR HELP.
YOU GUYS GET OUT SAFE.
[grunting]
GENNAI!
EH?
KUROBE,
WHERE'S GOJIRO?
HE'S OK.
IS THE POWER
WORKING YET?
WE'LL SEE
IN A COUPLE SECONDS.
GREAT GOING THERE, GENNAI.
ALL RIGHT!
I KNEW I COULD
FIX EVERYTHING!
OK, LET'S GET BACK
TO THE STATION.
HUH?
Kurobe: THIS CAN'T BE.
THE WIND'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE FROM THE SOUTH!
IT'S NO USE.
WE'RE SCREWED NOW.
GENNAI, INJECT
YOURSELF WITH THIS.
IT'LL
KEEP YOU ALIVE.
I ALREADY DID IT
TO MYSELF.
NOW HURRY UP.
YOU'RE A GOOD FRIEND,
KUROBE.
[groans]
GENNAI!
COME ON. LET'S GET
THIS THING MOVING.
IS THAT GENNAI?
IT WAS JUST
A LITTLE WIND,
THAT'S ALL.
Gojiro: DO YOU KNOW
HOW TO DRIVE THIS THING?
YEAH. I'VE DONE IT
SEVERAL TIMES
IN A VIDEO GAME.
I JUST SWITCH ON
ALL THE BUTTONS,
[buzzer]
HMM?
WHAT'S THAT
BUZZER MEAN?
Gennai: IT MEANS
SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH THE BATTERIES.
THEY'RE PROBABLY
EITHER DEAD OR
JUST NEED A CHARGE.
IN ANY CASE, THE TRAIN
WON'T BUDGE UNLESS
THEY'RE FULLY CHARGED.
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
ANY OF THAT MUCH LONGER,
'CAUSE IT'S HERE.
THE WIND
IS RIGHT ON CUE.
DAMN. WE DON'T
HAVE A PRAYER.
SHIT. COME ON!
MOVE!
WE DIDN'T
GO THROUGH
SO MUCH TROUBLE
ONLY TO GET
THIS FAR.
EVERY ONE OF US
HAS RISKED
EVERYTHING
AND GIVEN OUR ALL.
MOVE.
PLEASE MOVE.
[grunts]
COME ON! I CAN'T--
WE CAN'T--
WE WON'T DIE HERE.
[train horn honks]
[gasps]
IT STARTED.
IT'S WORKING! [laughs]
[laughs]
[chuckles]
WELL, HOW 'BOUT THAT,
HARUTO?
[Gojiro laughs]
DAD DID IT, IBUKI!
[chuckles]
HMM. [gasps]
THE RAILWAY
SIGNAL!
Gojiro: WHAT?
[grunts]
HARUTO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
YOU'RE HURT!
[panting]
Haruto: NARUSE...
[gasps]
FOLLOW ALONG THE PATH
YOU BELIEVE IN.
[train horn blows]
DAMN IT.
PLEASE,
LET ME HELP YOU.
[sighs]
THANK YOU,
COMMANDER KUNIKIDA.
HARUTO!
HUH?
DON'T STOP!
KEEP GOING!
THE WIND
IS COMING!
[yells]
[train horn blows]
IBARA NARUSE...
THAT GIRL LOOKED
INTO MY GROTESQUE FACE
AND SAID THAT
I WAS STILL HUMAN.
I WANT TO THANK
YOU PEOPLE.
THANKS TO YOU,
I CAN DIE A HUMAN BEING.
NARU...SE.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Taeko: THE WORDS LEFT BEHIND...
THE LAST BATTLE...
AN ANGEL...
YOUR SMILE...
THE BLINK OF AN EYE...
A WORLD COVERED IN WHITE...
A MOVING DOLL...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
PROMISE.