[wind blowing]
[birds chirping]
[footsteps]
[sighs]
Girl:
IBARA!
HOLD UP
FOR A MINUTE, IBARA!
[girls panting]
YOU'RE WALKING
WAY TOO FAST.
STOP FOOLING AROUND,
YOU TWO.
COME ON.
IBARA.
LET'S STOP.
JEEZ.
I DON'T WANT
TO WALK ANYMORE!
YEAH, ME, TOO.
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
SEE?
HEY, THE SIGN!
WE'VE MADE IT!
[laughs]
HMM.
OH, YEAH!
WE FINALLY MADE IT.
[laughing]
Girl:
I KNOW.
LET'S TAKE
A PICTURE.
Second girl:
WHAT? I DON'T THINK
THERE'S TIME.
OH, COME ON.
GET IN.
[cell phone buzzing]
IBARA, COME GET
IN THE SHOT.
VICE PRINCIPAL?
Man:
WHAT'S YOUR POSITION?
WE'VE JUST ARRIVED
AT ONE
OF THE 23 WARDS, SIR.
AND WHAT DO YOU
SEE AROUND YOU?
FIELDS, A SCHOOL,
A HOSPITAL.
THERE'S A POND,
A STEEL TOWER,
AND UTILITY POLES,
SOME CUMULONIMBUS CLOUDS,
TREES,
OFFICE BUILDINGS,
A SCARECROW.
Vice Principal:
ARE THERE ANY PEOPLE NEARBY?
Ibara:
NOT A SINGLE SOUL.
CONTINUE TO THE CENTER
OF THE CITY.
PHONES WON'T WORK THERE,
SO SWITCH TO YOUR RADIOS.
YES, SIR.
ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO,
LET'S GET GOING,
SHALL WE?
BUT, IBARA.
YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
STOP WORRYING SO MUCH.
JUST THINK OF IT
AS A FIELD TRIP.
TIME FOR
SOME SIGHTSEEING
IN THE OLD CAPITAL.
["Angel" by angela playing]
[footsteps]
Ibara: FIRST WE NEED
TO CROSS THE RIVER.
IT'S DOWN THIS ROAD.
ARE WE GOING TO WALK
THE WHOLE TIME WE'RE HERE?
WHY CAN'T THEY JUST
SEARCH FROM THE SKY
OR SOMETHING?
Ibara: DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT WE LEARNED IN SCHOOL?
THEY CAN'T SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON
IN THE CITY
FROM UP THERE,
SO SOMEBODY'S
GOT TO GO INSIDE
AND INVESTIGATE IT
FROM THE GROUND.
I GUESS THAT DOES
MAKE SOME SENSE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
WE HAVE TO MINDLESSLY
WALK AROUND
A PLACE LIKE THIS.
WE'RE NOT PUPPETS,
YOU KNOW.
WE STILL HAVE
TO DO THE JOB WE'RE
ASSIGNED TO DO, AOI.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT ARE THERE PEOPLE
REALLY LIVING
OUT HERE STILL?
WELL, WHO KNOWS?
OUR JOB IS TO FIND OUT.
[radio static, beeps]
Ibara: YES?
VICE PRINCIPAL?
Vice Principal:
WE'VE JUST PICKED UP
A RADIO SIGNAL.
IT'S AN S.O.S.
[girls gasp]
IT'S WITHIN
A FIVE-KILOMETER RADIUS
OF YOUR POSITION.
SO THERE ARE PEOPLE
NEARBY? HERE?
Vice Principal:
IT'S POSSIBLE, YES.
FIND AN OPEN AREA
TO SET A SMOKE FLARE.
Ibara: YES, SIR.
WHAT DO WE DO
ONCE WE FIND THEM?
DON'T DO ANYTHING.
[gasps]
ALL YOU NEED TO DO
IS FIND THEM.
[radio static]
[footsteps]
WHY WAS THERE AN S.O.S.
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
THERE'S BEEN
A DRASTIC INCREASE
IN THE PAST MONTH.
CONSIDERING
THE DANGER,
THEY MUST HAVE
HAD A GOOD REASON
TO STAY BEHIND.
COMMANDER,
WE WILL SOON
BE FLYING OVER
OUR TARGET AREA.
10 MINUTES.
MY TITLE
IS VICE PRINCIPAL
AT THE NATIONAL DEFENSE
ACADEMY TECHNICAL SCHOOL.
JUST CALL ME THAT.
NOW HAVE EVERYONE
SUIT UP.
YES, SIR!
[door closes]
[panting]
WOW!
[laughs]
THAT RIVER
IS HUMONGOUS.
THE WIND
FEELS NICE.
[laughing]
Aoi: WOW.
THE WATER'S ALL SPARKLY.
HEY, GUYS,
COME CHECK IT OUT.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
WHY DON'T WE STOP HERE
AND TAKE
A SMALL BREAK TO EAT?
I MEAN, IT'S WAY
PAST LUNCHTIME ALREADY.
I GUESS WE CAN.
THIS AREA
IS BIG ENOUGH FOR
THE VICE PRINCIPAL
TO LAND
HIS HELICOPTER.
ALL RIGHT!
HMM.
YOU'RE REALLY GOING
TO EAT ALL OF THAT?
THERE'S SO MUCH.
OH, MY GOD!
IT'S SO YUMMY!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THIS IS, A PICNIC?
[gasps]
W-WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
I JUST GAVE MYSELF
A SHOT
OF PURE NUTRITION.
IT'S EASIER THAN EATING,
DON'T YOU THINK?
BUT THAT'S--
THAT'S LIKE...
WHAT IS IT, AOI?
IT'S NOTHING!
AH, THESE RICE BALLS
ARE DELICIOUS! MMM!
SO ARE THE SAUSAGES
AND THE CRAB
CROQUETTES. MMM!
IT'S ALL SO GOOD!
I LOVE BEING HUMAN!
IT'S THE BEST! MMM.
THERE IT IS.
LAND NEXT
TO THE RED SMOKE.
[man gasping]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
YEAH. IT SOUNDED NEARBY.
IBARA,
COME TAKE A LOOK!
IT'S A PERSON.
[gasping]
H-HE SOUNDS LIKE HE'S
REALLY IN PAIN, IBARA.
BUT YOU HEARD
THE VICE PRINCIPAL.
RIGHT. HE TOLD US
NOT TO DO ANYTHING.
[beeping]
LOOK AT THIS.
THE COUNTER IS SHOWING
ABNORMALLY HIGH LEVELS
OF CONTAMINATION.
THEY'RE COMING
FROM OVER THERE,
NEAR THE GUY
IN THE HAZMAT SUIT.
[gasping]
HELP...
[whimpering]
Man: PLEASE, SOMEONE,
HELP!
TAEKO.
[gasps]
GO GET ME
THE FIRST-AID KIT.
[gasps]
BUT WE'RE SUPPOSED TO WAIT
FOR THE VICE PRINCIPAL.
TO HELL
WITH THE RULES.
I'M GOING IN.
[gasping]
IMPOSSIBLE.
WHERE'S HER MASK?
[gasping]
I'M GOING TO FIX YOU
RIGHT UP.
MY GUN IS LOADED
WITH A MEDICINE
CALLED AETHER.
IT'S A CURE-ALL.
HOLD STILL.
[gun clicks]
[dart thwips]
[bubbling]
THERE. THAT SHOULD
START TO MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
[continues gasping]
W-WHAT ARE YOU?
AN ANGEL?
IBARA'S HELPING
THE SURVIVOR, SIR.
BRING HIM IN. HURRY.
Man: YES, SIR!
BRING HIM IN
RIGHT AWAY!
Second man:
BRINGING HIM IN
RIGHT AWAY!
[footsteps]
Vice Principal:
WHAT WERE YOU
THINKING, NARUSE?
THE AETHER'S
INTENDED FOR
MINOR CASES.
IT'LL JUST GIVE HIM
TEMPORARY RELIEF
AT BEST.
AND WITH THE LIMITED
QUANTITIES WE HAVE,
WE CAN'T
AFFORD TO WASTE IT
ON PEOPLE LIKE HIM.
[groans]
I KNEW IT!
THEN YOU SHOULD
MAKE MORE OF IT!
I INTEND TO TREAT
EVERY LIVING PERSON
WE FIND.
THAT WHAT WE'VE
BEEN TASKED
TO DO, ANYWAY.
[rotors whirring]
[gasps]
WHO ARE THOSE GIRLS?
HOW CAN THEY SURVIVE
WITHOUT WEARING
ANY MASKS
OR HAZMAT SUITS?
Vice Principal:
THEY ARE KNOWN...
AS COPPELION.
THEY HAVE BEEN
GENETICALLY ENGINEERED
TO HAVE
A STRONG RESISTANCE
TO THIS TYPE OF HARSH,
DANGEROUS ENVIRONMENT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH THE TWO OF YOU NOW?
NOTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT
IF NORMAL PEOPLE
CAN'T SURVIVE
IN THIS ENVIRONMENT,
DOES THAT MEAN
THAT WE'RE...
YOU KNOW?
THAT WE'RE
PUPPETS AFTER ALL?
OH. [chuckles]
DON'T BE SILLY.
WOULD A PUPPET
LOVE TO EAT AS MUCH
AS YOU LIKE TO?
[gasps]
[giggles]
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
WAIT UP, IBARA!
[giggles]
OH, THAT RICE BALL...
Vice Principal:
THE OLD CAPITAL
IS THE WORLD'S
LARGEST GHOST TOWN,
AND THESE THREE GIRLS
ARE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN SURVIVE FREELY
WITHIN IT.
[sighs]
[yawns]
[bird tweeting]
[wings flutter]
[sighs]
MORNING
IN THE OLD CAPITAL.
[footsteps]
HEY.
OH, HEY THERE,
IBARA. WERE YOU ABLE
TO GET ANY SLEEP
AT ALL LAST NIGHT?
WANT SOME BREAKFAST?
I'VE GOT
A LOT OF GOOD STUFF
IN HERE.
[sighs]
HUH?
[yawns]
Taeko: IBARA!
COME OVER HERE!
WHAT IS IT? YOU OK?
LOOK,
OVER THERE.
IT'S A DOG.
I THINK
IT FOLLOWED ME.
WHOA, YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT THE
CONTAMINATION
DOESN'T BOTHER
HIM EITHER.
Ibara: YEAH,
LOOKS THAT WAY.
IT PROBABLY ADAPTED
TO THIS ENVIRONMENT.
ACTUALLY THERE ARE
BIRDS HERE AS WELL.
THANK GOODNESS WE'RE
NOT THE ONLY ONES
OUT HERE.
[scoffs] ARE YOU
LUMPING US IN
WITH A BUNCH OF
STRAY ANIMALS?
YES, I AM.
ALL CREATURES
ARE ONE FAMILY.
WE NEED
TO GET MOVING.
THE S.O.S. CALLS
ARE CONCENTRATED
IN THIS AREA.
HOWEVER, NOBODY SEEMS
TO BE RESPONDING
TO OUR OUTGOING SIGNALS.
THEY MIGHT BE INJURED
OR JUST CAN'T MOVE.
THEN HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO FIND THEM?
WE'LL USE THE COUNTER.
WITH ITS SENSITIVITY
SET TO GO ALL THE WAY
UP TO MAXIMUM,
WE'LL RECEIVE
REALLY STRONG SIGNALS
IF SOMETHING IS NEARBY,
WHETHER IT'S AN ANIMAL
OF IF THEY'RE HUMAN.
[counter beeping]
Aoi: HEY, IBARA,
CAN'T WE
DO SOMETHING
ABOUT HAVING TO
WALK EVERYWHERE?
WE NEED A CAR!
IT'S A MODERN
NECESSITY!
THE ONLY KIND OF CAR
THAT WE'D BE
ABLE TO FIND
AROUND THIS PLACE
IS AN OLD CLUNKER.
AS SOON AS YOU
START THE THING UP,
BOOM!
[gasps]
THEN WE SHOULD ASK
THE VICE PRINCIPAL
TO GET US
A SHINY NEW ONE,
ONE WITH A SHOWER
AND A FRIDGE IN IT.
LOOK, ON THE TV.
I AM COLONEL
ONIHEI MISHIMA,
VICE PRINCIPAL
OF THE GROUND
SELF-DEFENSE FORCE,
THIRD DIVISION'S
TECHNICAL SCHOOL.
I'VE BEEN ASSIGNED
TO COMMAND THIS MISSION.
NO WAY!
OUR VICE PRINCIPAL'S
ON THE TV!
SO CRAZY!
HE'S A CELEBRITY!
SO, VICE PRINCIPAL,
HOW DO YOU ADDRESS
THE SAFETY
OF THE SELF-DEFENSE
FORCE SOLDIERS
ON THIS TEAM?
WE HAVE
THE BARRIER SUIT.
IT WAS DEVELOPED
TO PROTECT AGAINST
THE HARSHEST CONDITIONS.
TESTS HAVE PROVEN
THEY'RE 99% EFFECTIVE.
OF COURSE THE LAST 1%
IS ALWAYS ON OUR MINDS.
TURN THAT THING OFF.
IT DOESN'T APPLY
TO US, ANYWAY.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
Announcer: THANK YOU
FOR THIS RARE VIDEO FOOTAGE,
VICE PRINCIPAL MISHIMA.
THIS CONCLUDES
OUR LIVE BROADCAST.
WAIT. WE HAVE TIME
TO GO TO THE EPICENTER.
[gasps]
WE'D LIKE
THE WHOLE NATION
TO SEE THE STATE
OF THE OLD CAPITAL.
I WONDER WHAT EXACTLY
IS GOING ON RIGHT NOW
DOWN AT THE EPICENTER.
I'VE HEARD
THAT PEOPLE CAN'T
GO ANYWHERE NEAR IT
BECAUSE IT'S
SO CONTAMINATED.
BUT SOMEONE IS
MONITORING IT, RIGHT?
WHO CARES, ANYWAY?
I SAY WE STAY
IN A HOTEL!
HEY, IBARA,
DON'T YOU THINK
WE DESERVE IT
AFTER COMING
ALL THIS WAY?
LOOK AT THAT HOTEL, AOI.
HOW'S THAT?
[gasps]
SERIOUSLY?
THAT HOTEL IS
FALLING OVER!
THIS CITY SUFFERED
A CATASTROPHE,
AND WE ARE
JUST ABLE TO SEE
ALL OF ITS SCARS.
Man: THE FOG SURE
IS THICK TODAY.
WE PROBABLY
WON'T EVEN BE ABLE
TO SEE THE COFFIN.
IBUSE, PUT US THROUGH
TO THE TV STATION.
[gasps]
YES, SIR,
BUT DON'T BLAME ME
IF SOMETHING GOES WRONG.
HOW ARE THINGS LOOKING,
VICE PRINCIPAL?
Mishima:
FOR MOST OF THE DAY,
A THICK FOG SURROUNDS
THE EPICENTER,
OBSCURING OUR VIEW.
THIS FOG IS
ACTUALLY A CLUSTER
OF FINE PARTICLES
KNOWN AS HOT PARTICLES.
THEY GET PICKED UP
BY THE SEA BREEZE,
MIX WITH THE MOISTURE
IN THE AIR,
AND FORM A MIST.
Announcer:
DO THESE HOT PARTICLES
MEAN THAT
THE EPICENTER IS STILL
HIGHLY CONTAMINATED?
THAT IS CORRECT.
A PERSON
COULD NOT SURVIVE
ANYWHERE WITHIN
OR EVEN AROUND IT.
Announcer: I SEE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'D HAVE TO USE
A ROBOT OR THE LIKE
TO BE ABLE
TO EXAMINE THE SITE.
[sighs]
Mishima:
THE FOG, IT'S CLEARING.
[gasps]
[beeping]
WE'VE GOT 50 SECONDS.
WE CAN'T STAY
ANY LONGER THAN THAT.
Mishima:
CITIZENS OF JAPAN,
PLEASE STOP
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
FOR JUST A MOMENT,
AND TAKE A LOOK
AT YOUR TV SETS.
IN ONE DAY,
THE WHOLE WORLD CHANGED.
WHY DID THIS HAPPEN?
COULD WE HAVE DONE
ANYTHING TO PREVENT IT?
WHAT YOU'RE SEEING NOW
IS THE EPICENTER
THAT DESTROYED 90%
OF THE OLD CAPITAL.
SO, CITIZENS OF JAPAN--
NO, PEOPLE OF THE WORLD,
PANDORA'S BOX HAS BEEN
OPENED BY HUMAN HANDS.
OUR PROBLEM NOW
IS WE DON'T KNOW
HOW TO CLOSE IT.
[wind blowing]
LET'S GO.
OUR JOB IS
TO FIND PEOPLE.
Y-YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S GO!
HUH?
THAT TALL TOWER,
WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S A PLANT
OF SOME KIND, I THINK.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT PLACE
IS CRAZY HUGE.
IT'S WAY BIGGER
THAN THE PRISON
NEXT TO IT.
Aoi: OH, MY GOD!
THIS PLACE IS
FREAKING HUMONGOUS!
LOOK HOW FAR DOWN
IT GOES.
IT'S LIKE A TOWN
UNTO ITSELF.
[chuckles]
[footsteps]
[counter beeping]
HUH? HEY,
THE NUMBERS
ON THE COUNTER
HAVE
REALLY SPIKED.
IS IT A PERSON?
WAIT. IT POINTS
TO WHERE WE CAME FROM.
THAT'S THE SAME DOG
FROM THIS MORNING.
Taeko: HE MUST HAVE
FOLLOWED US HERE.
HMM. HOW MANY
MORE DISTRACTIONS
WILL THERE BE?
HE'S GOING
TO KEEP US
FROM FINDING
THE PEOPLE
WE NEED TO HELP.
I'LL GO TALK TO HIM
SO HE'LL STAY HERE
AND BE OUT OF OUR WAY.
THIS IS
THE PERFECT JOB FOR ME,
BECAUSE I
MANAGED THE ANIMALS
BACK AT THE SCHOOL.
ALL RIGHT.
IF WE FIND ANYONE,
WE'LL COME BACK
FOR YOU.
Ibara:
KEEP YOUR RADIO ON.
WE'LL BE
ON CHANNEL TWO.
OK.
HEY, IBARA,
HOW IS SHE SO GOOD
WITH ANIMALS?
WELL, SHE'S
GOOD WITH THEM
BECAUSE
IT WAS WRITTEN
RIGHT INTO HER
GENETIC CODING.
SHE WAS BORN WITH
THE ENHANCED SENSES
OF AN ANIMAL.
[counter beeping]
[sighs] THE ALARM'S
GOING AGAIN.
[beeping continues]
DO YOU SEE ANYONE,
IBARA?
[beeping intensifies]
HEY.
Ibara: SHIT.
[flies buzzing]
WE'RE TOO LATE.
[gasps]
YOU STAY RIGHT THERE,
AOI.
SUICIDE.
HE'S BEEN DEAD
OVER A MONTH.
[Aoi whimpers]
I CAN'T
TAKE THIS!
I WANT TO GO HOME.
I'M SCARED.
[whimpers]
HMM?
[gasps]
IBARA, LOOK OUT!
[growling]
IBARA!
[snarls]
[yelps]
[screams]
I TRANQUILIZED HIM.
IS HE OUT?
Y-YEAH. I THINK SO.
IS IT THE SAME DOG,
THE ONE THAT
WAS FOLLOWING US?
NO, THIS ISN'T
THAT DOG.
TAKE A LOOK
AT ITS FANGS.
[soft breathing]
THIS IS A WOLF.
WHAT WOULD
A WOLF BE DOING HERE
INSIDE OF THE CITY?
STRAY DOGS PROBABLY
BECAME FERAL.
THIS WHOLE PLACE TURNED INTO
A WILD FOREST AFTER ALL.
[gasps] THAT MEANS
THAT TAEKO,
THE DOG SHE'S WITH
COULD ALSO
BE A WOLF!
[gasps]
AND SHE'S
COMPLETELY UNARMED.
[static]
Ibara:
HEY, TAEKO, ANSWER ME!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
I KNEW IT.
I KNEW SOMETHING BAD
WOULD HAPPEN
IF WE CAME
OUT HERE!
[crying]
PEOPLE JUST DON'T
BELONG IN THIS CITY
ANYMORE!
LET'S GO.
[stops crying]
JUST STAY STRONG.
TAEKO NEEDS OUR HELP.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Ibara: A MISSING CHILD...
A GENTLE GAZE...
A MOTHER...
A PUPPET WITHOUT COMPASSION...
A PERSON TO PROTECT...
A PROMISE...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
FUTURE.