ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S THE PLAN, GUYS.
THE DIVERSION TEAM'S
INITIAL TASK
WILL BE TO DRAW OUT
THE FIRST DIVISION.
ONCE WE ARE
A KILOMETER AWAY
FROM THE PLANET,
WE'LL SET OFF
A SMOKE FLARE.
THE WHITE SMOKE WILL
LET THE MAINTENANCE TEAM
KNOW IT'S TIME FOR THEM
TO HEAD TOWARDS
THE TRAIN STATION.
WAIT. WHY DON'T WE
JUST USE THE RADIOS
TO COMMUNICATE?
WE CAN'T.
THE OZU SISTERS
ARE USING
THE SAME RADIO
WE DO.
Ibara: ONCE
THE MAINTENANCE TEAM
HAS THE TRAIN
UP AND RUNNING,
THEY WILL APPROACH
THIS STATION
[horn blares]
AND SOUND THE HORN.
OUR DIVERSION TEAM
WILL FIRST NEUTRALIZE
THE OZU SISTERS,
JUMP ONTO THE TRAIN,
AND THEN ESCAPE
FROM THE ZONE
WITH EVERYONE ELSE.
THAT INCLUDES
MISS IBUKI'S HUSBAND,
OF COURSE.
WE'RE COUNTING
ON YOU, IBARA.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
EVERYONE MOVE OUT!
["Angel" by angela playing]
Ibara: DON'T GO
TOO FAST, HARUTO.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THE OZU SISTERS
ACTUALLY SEE US.
[gasping]
Haruto:
WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH FUKASAKU AND
THE OZU SISTERS?
OZU SISTERS.
Ibara: WELL, YOU SEE...
[wails]
GIVE IT BACK TO ME!
I'M HUNGRY! GIVE ME
MY LUNCH BACK!
IF YOU WANT IT BACK,
YOU'LL HAVE TO RUN NAKED
AROUND THE SCHOOLYARD.
[Ozu sisters laugh]
SHE WAS BULLIED, HUH?
HEY, SHE
WAS SEVERELY
TRAUMATIZED.
WHERE ARE WE?
No-sense: WARNING.
LIFE SIGNS DETECTED
UP AHEAD.
IS THAT
NO-SENSE SPEAKING?
HEY, IT IS YOU!
WHOO-HOO!
THIS ROCKS!
Shion: HEY!
[gasps]
I THOUGHT
I KNEW THAT VOICE.
LONG TIME NO SEE,
AOI FUKASAKU.
[whimpers]
[beeps]
OK, WE'RE A KILOMETER
AWAY FROM THE PLANET.
GOOD. STEP ON IT!
[giggles]
HERE THEY COME.
OPEN FIRE!
[giggles]
[chuckles]
[Shion laughs]
LOOK AT THE WHITE SMOKE.
ARMORED CARRIER ZERO,
OZU SISTERS ONE.
DON'T EVEN THINK YOU
CAN ESCAPE FROM US.
LET'S GET 'EM.
AYE, AYE, SIR.
[yawns]
HUH?
Gennai: THE SMOKE.
THAT'S OUR SIGNAL
TO MOVE OUT.
Kurobe: FINALLY!
NICE MOVE, HARUTO.
THEY'RE CHASING US
JUST LIKE WE WANTED.
HANG IN THERE,
MISS IBUKI.
Ayame:
HAS HER WATER
BROKEN YET?
NO, BUT SHE LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S IN A LOT OF PAIN.
REMEMBER, IT'S
JUST THE PAIN
OF CHILDBIRTH.
SO WHY ARE
WE LEAVING
THE ARMORED
CARRIER?
IF WE
WALK AROUND ON FOOT,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO LURE
THE OZU SISTERS CLOSER.
I CONCUR.
[whimpers]
Kurobe: ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE HERE.
GET TO IT, GENNAI.
[crow cawing]
EH, FOUND IT.
THERE'S THE BREAK
IN THE LINE.
[gasping]
[yells]
UH, WHAT WAS THAT SOUND?
THAT WAS HER WATER
BREAKING, SILLY.
OK, TIME TO DELIVER
THE BABY.
ARE YOU READY?
YOU BET I AM.
I'M COUNTING
ON YOU, TAEKO.
Taeko: I'LL DO MY BEST.
I PROMISE.
I HAVE JUST
DETECTED THE ENEMY
ENTERING THE PARK.
THANK YOU,
NO-SENSE.
WITH
KANON'S ABILITY,
IT'S NOT
GONNA BE THAT LONG
BEFORE THEY FIND US.
I HOPE
YOU HAVE SOME SORT
OF A PLAN IN MIND.
HMM...
YOU GOTTA
BE KIDDING.
HOW DID
YOU EVER GET ELECTED
AS CLASS PRESIDENT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
THIS TOOK ME
ALL NIGHT TO MAKE.
IT'S A NEW TYPE
OF BOMB.
IT'S REALLY
A BOMB?
IT KIND OF
LOOKS MORE LIKE
A MISSILE TO ME.
JUST WATCH THIS.
WOW.
IT TOTALLY SPLIT UP.
THAT'S EXACTLY
HOW THAT THING'S
SUPPOSED TO WORK.
[clacking]
Kurobe:
THERE WE GO.
IBUKI...
HANG IN THERE.
[wind blowing]
HMM?
[gasps]
LOOK AT THE SKY.
IT'S FILLING UP
WITH HEAVY, DARK CLOUDS.
[gasps]
CAN WE MAKE IT IN TIME?
I'D SAY
WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
Kanon: WHERE'D YOU GO?
YOU CAN'T HIDE
FROM US FOR LONG.
HMM.
THEY'RE IN THE BUSHES.
GO LOOK.
ARE YOU SURE?
IT COULD BE
A TRAP.
DON'T WORRY, SHION.
I'LL ZAP 'EM
WITH MY ELECTRICITY
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS.
[gasps]
AWESOME, SIS!
[giggles]
I'M GONNA TEAR YOU
APART LIMB BY LIMB
WITH MY BARE HANDS.
BETTER YET,
I'LL JUST STOMP YA!
HUH? HEY, SIS,
THERE'S A STRANGE
ORANGE BALL
DOWN HERE.
WHOA.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I CALL THEM
ELECTRIC MINES.
I DESIGNED THEM TO EMIT
ELECTRICAL SIGNALS
SIMILAR TO THOSE
OF BIOELECTRICITY,
AND NOW THEY'RE SCATTERED
THROUGHOUT THE PARK.
THEY SHOULD CONFUSE
KANON'S ABILITY
TO DETECT HER ENEMY
ACCURATELY.
[No-sense whirring]
OH. LOOK AT THAT,
IBARA.
HALT!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HUH?
HMM?
[groans]
I'M TIRED OF THIS CHASE.
WE'RE GOING TO HEAD OUT
TO THE SARCOPHAGUS NOW.
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
THEY'RE BAILING OUT
ON THE CHASE
AND ARE HEADED
TO THE SARCOPHAGUS.
WHA?
WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
WE NEED
TO DO SOMETHING
TO TRY AND ATTRACT
THEIR ATTENTION
SO THAT THEY...
[gasps] WAIT.
WHY ARE YOU LOOKING AT ME
THAT WAY, IBARA?
YOU WANT ME TO DO WHAT?!
THAT'S LIKE
COMMITTING SUICIDE!
YOU USED
TO GET BULLIED
BY THE OZU SISTERS
IN SCHOOL.
IF THEY SEE YOU,
THEN THEY'LL
UNDOUBTEDLY
COME AFTER YOU.
TAKE HER FOR A RIDE,
NO-SENSE.
WAIT.
DON'T LISTEN TO HER!
I'M TELLING YOU THEY'RE
GOING TO KILL ME!
STOP, YOU STUPID ROBOT!
STOP!
[yelling]
[coughs]
FINALLY YOU STOPPED.
Kanon: HEY THERE.
[gasps]
THIS IS
A NICE SURPRISE.
BEFORE WE GET
TO THE SARCOPHAGUS,
LET'S BEAT THE CRAP
OUT OF THIS LITTLE WUSS.
IT'S WORKING.
THE OZU SISTERS
ARE STARTING
TO TAKE THE BAIT.
[wind blowing]
CHECK IT OUT.
DO YOU SEE THOSE CLOUDS?
THE WIND IS STARTING
TO PICK UP.
BUT IT WAS SUNNY
JUST A FEW
MINUTES AGO.
WE'RE DOWN NOW
TO MAYBE SEVEN
OR EIGHT HOURS AT THE MOST.
SEVEN OR EIGHT HOURS?
THEN WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO GET THE TRAIN
UP AND RUNNING
A LOT FASTER THAN
WE PLANNED. GREAT.
Kanon: COME BACK HERE,
YOU TWERP!
[yelling]
YOU WON'T GET AWAY,
YOU LITTLE RAT!
HA HA!
HARUTO,
WHAT TIME YOU GOT?
0900 HOURS.
WE'VE GOT
UNTIL SUNSET.
DAMN THAT AOI FUKASAKU.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
SHE'S GONE OFF TO,
BUT I'M GONNA FIND HER,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
AW, JEEZ.
I KNEW
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
GONE OUTSIDE AGAIN.
I WANNA GO BACK
TO THE PLANET'S
STOREROOM.
MISS AOI, THAT WOULD
NOT DO YOU ANY GOOD
OR SOLVE ANYTHING.
YOU MUST REMAIN STRONG
AND OVERCOME THE OBSTACLES
THAT ARE FACING YOU.
STOP LECTURING ME,
ALREADY!
THERE ARE THINGS
IN THIS WORLD
THAT I CAN'T
DO ANYTHING ABOUT!
I THINK I SEE...
NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
I CAN'T WIN AGAINST
THOSE TWO SISTERS!
THAT IS NOT TRUE.
THE WORLD IS
A DARK AND SAD PLACE
ONLY IF YOU MAKE IT OUT
TO BE LIKE THAT.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
NO-SENSE,
BEHIND YOU!
HAH!
[gasps]
[laughing]
YOU PIECE OF JUNK.
I'LL MAKE SCRAP
OUT OF YOU!
TAKE THAT AND
THAT AND THAT!
STOP. STOP BEATING HIM.
JUST LOOKING
AT YOUR FACE
PISSES ME OFF,
YOU HUMAN WANNABE.
I SAID STOP!
BITCH, WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO?
YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR.
I'LL TAKE YOU ON NOW.
THAT'S SURPRISING
COMING FROM YOU.
YOU'RE NORMALLY
SUCH A WHINY BABY.
SO YOU
WANNA FIGHT ME,
AOI FUKASAKU?
PLEASE, GET AWAY,
MISS AOI.
PLAYTIME IS OVER.
I'M GONNA POUND YOU
STRAIGHT DOWN INTO HELL!
UH...
HUH?
EH?
[gasps]
I'M GONNA FALL.
[screams]
UH...
PLEASE GET AWAY,
MISS AOI.
LET GO OF ME,
YOU FREAKIN' SCRAP HEAP!
Shion:
THAT HURTS!
DAMN IT!
[pedals squeaking]
THAT DOES IT.
I'M GONNA GET YOU.
YOU ARE
SO FREAKIN' DEAD.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
[gunfire]
[yelps]
SORRY
WE'RE LATE!
GET OUT OF HERE,
AOI!
[squealing]
Shion: HEY, SIS!
WHY THE HELL ARE YOU
JUST STANDING THERE?!
SHOOT YOUR ELECTRICITY!
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
Haruto: KANON OZU'S
MAJOR WEAKNESS IS WATER.
IF SHE FIRES OFF
TOO NEAR IT,
SHE'LL ELECTROCUTE HERSELF.
Ibara: REALLY?
THAT'S INFORMATION
WE CAN USE.
COME ON.
WHY ARE YOU BEING SUCH
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING, SIS!
EH! THAT BRIDGE
IS IN THE WAY.
HOW THE HECK
AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET PAST IT?
STUPID PARK. REALLY?
HOLD IT, SWAN!
[yelps]
THAT SHOULD BE
A BIG ENOUGH GAP!
SLIP ON THROUGH,
AOI.
THIS IS NO WAY
TO SPEND TIME
AT A PARK.
I'LL LEAVE THAT ONE
TO MY LITTLE SISTER.
NO-SENSE,
ARE YOU OK?
YOU'RE NOT
LOOKING SO GOOD.
W-WHAT ABOUT
MISS AOI?
SHE'S HEADED
TO THE WEST.
I'M WORRIED BECAUSE
SHE'S BY HERSELF.
NO-SENSE WILL GO...
PROTECT MISS AOI.
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
COME BACK HERE!
HE'S ACTING UNDER
HIS OWN FREE WILL.
WE DON'T HAVE
ANY TIME TO REST
HERE, NARUSE.
THE WIND IS
GETTING CLOSER
BY THE MINUTE.
Haruto:
WE'RE HERE TO RESCUE
THE PREGNANT WOMAN'S
HUSBAND, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
ACCORDING TO
MISS IBUKI,
HE'S WITH
THE FIRST
DIVISION.
Soldier: HEY,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
SIR, IT'S A RADIO
THE COPPELION
WERE USING.
REALLY? LET'S STAY
ON THIS CHANNEL.
[radio whines]
ANYONE THERE?
THIS IS GRANNY AYAME.
PICK UP. IS SHE SHOWING
SIGNS OF DILATING YET?
Taeko: NO,
NOT THAT I CAN TELL.
SHOULD I GIVE HER SOME
LABOR-INDUCING DRUGS?
ABSOLUTELY NOT!
YOU YOUNG PEOPLE
RELY TOO QUICKLY
ON MEDICINES!
WHAT THE HELL
IS ALL THIS ABOUT?
Ayame: SHE'LL BE FINE...
IT SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE SOMEONE'S
HAVING A BABY.
Officer:
WHAT NONSENSE.
LET'S GO.
Ayame: WHAT DID
YOU JUST SAY?
Taeko: MISS IBUKI
IS TERRIBLY ANEMIC,
EVEN THOUGH SHE SAYS
SHE'S BEEN TAKING
MEDICATIONS
TO BUILD UP
HER BLOOD.
HOW LONG
HAS SHE BEEN ON THEM?
SHE SAYS SINCE
HER FIRST TRIMESTER.
THE FETUS MUST BE
ABSORBING HUGE AMOUNTS
OF THE MOTHER'S
NUTRIENT INTAKE.
I'LL BET THE BABY'S
GOING TO BE A BIG ONE.
[gasps]
I THINK THAT'S HIM.
[brush rustles]
HUH?
YOU'RE MISS IBUKI'S
HUSBAND,
AREN'T YOU, SIR?
PLEASE, YOU'VE
GOTTA COME WITH US.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT
HELPED OUR FRIEND AOI
ESCAPE, RIGHT?
DAMN IT. DID WE
GET THE WRONG GUY?
PLEASE TELL ME...
WILL IBUKI AND THE BABY
BE ALL RIGHT?
THIS WHOLE AREA
WILL BE COVERED
WITH A CONCENTRATED
CONTAMINATION.
WE PROMISE
TO RESCUE YOUR FAMILY
AND TO MAKE SURE
THAT THEY'RE SAFE.
AND YOU, TOO, OF COURSE,
BECAUSE MISS IBUKI
ASKED US TO.
IBUKI DID?
HEY, IS SHE
A COPPELION?
[laughs]
WELL DONE,
COMRADE.
GET ME
THE HANDCUFFS.
DON'T PRESS YOUR LUCK,
YOU STUPID HUMANS!
STAND DOWN,
HARUTO!
[gasps]
DID YOU JUST SAY,
"HARUTO"?
CLASS PRESIDENT
IBARA NARUSE.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE
WE MEET AGAIN.
I CAN SENSE YOU HIDING
BACK THERE, YOU KNOW,
HARUTO KUROSAWA.
I'D SUGGEST YOU DON'T
TRY ANYTHING DANGEROUS
THAT YOU MIGHT REGRET.
OUR BELOVED
CLASS PRESIDENT
WOULD BE LIKELY
TO LOSE HER LIFE
IF YOU DID.
DROP YOUR WEAPONS
AND COME ON OUT.
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL,
YOU DON'T HAVE
THE STINK OF HUMANS
ALL OVER YOU
LIKE THIS ONE DOES.
YOU STILL POSSESS
THE NOBILITY
OF THE COPPELION
WITHIN YOU.
I'LL TAKE HER DOWN,
HARUTO,
SO DON'T LISTEN TO HER.
[growls]
[screaming]
[electricity crackling]
Haruto:
STOP IT, KANON!
HEH.
WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU WANT?
Officer: HE WAS CARRYING
ALL THESE WEAPONS?
[gasps]
HARUTO, RUN AWAY.
THIS IS THE DEAL.
YOU HAVE ONE
OF TWO SIMPLE CHOICES
TO MAKE HERE.
YOU CAN COME
JOIN ME AND SHION
AS WE STICK IT
TO THE HUMANS LIKE YOU
KNOW THEY DESERVE,
OR YOU CAN EXPERIENCE
THE POWER OF MY THUNDERBOLT
IN HER PLACE IF YOU'D LIKE.
COME TO YOUR SENSES,
KANON.
IF YOU'RE SEEKING
REVENGE ON THE HUMANS,
YOU SHOULD STOP
WASTING YOUR TIME.
LOOK AT THEIR HISTORY
TO UNDERSTAND WHY.
THEY CONTINUALLY
CREATE PATHS TO THEIR
OWN SELF-DESTRUCTION,
AND THEY'RE DOOMED TO
REPEAT THESE TRAGEDIES
INDEFINITELY.
LIKE I CARE.
TAKE THAT!
[thunder crashes]
[screaming]
THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN YOU DESPISED HUMANS,
HARUTO KUROSAWA.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
IT'S TRUE.
I DID DESPISE THEM,
BUT MY DNA
REFUSES TO LISTEN
TO MY LOGIC.
[gasps]
HARUTO.
HMPH.
I COULDN'T BE MORE
DISAPPOINTED IN YOU!
[grunts]
[gasps]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
RUN!
TRAITOR!
GET GOING!
Ibara: THANKS.
STOP, DAMN IT!
[groans]
YOU BETTER STOP!
I DON'T THINK SO.
[laughs] LOOKS LIKE
I CAUGHT UP, AOI FUKASAKU.
[squeals]
[screams]
HUH?
MISS AOI.
[gasps]
I AM SORRY
TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
OH, NO-SENSE,
THANK GOD YOU'RE OK!
Ibara: I WONDER IF AOI
GOT AWAY SAFELY.
[sighs]
THIS DIVERSION STUFF
ISN'T EASY.
HARUTO, ARE YOU OK?
THEY TOOK ALL
OF MY WEAPONS FROM ME.
AND ALL I HAVE
IS THIS GUN.
IBUKI AND I MET
HERE IN THIS PARK.
A CRAMPED SHELTER
WAS THE ONLY PLACE
WE COULD MEET.
WE BOTH KNEW THAT
OUR RELATIONSHIP
WAS FORBIDDEN.
FORBIDDEN?
WHY WOULD A RELATIONSHIP
BE FORBIDDEN?
BECAUSE I'M A MEMBER
OF THE FIRST DIVISION.
I'VE FORGOTTEN
WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE HUMAN
A LONG TIME AGO.
I'M A GHOST,
A GHOST THAT HAUNTS
THIS CITY.
THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE
WHERE I FIT IN,
BUT IBUKI IS DIFFERENT.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
BUT YOU'RE
DIFFERENT NOW
BECAUSE OF WHAT
SHE MEANS TO YOU,
AND THAT'S WHY YOU
WANT TO PROTECT HER.
YOU ARE NOT A GHOST.
YOU'RE
A LIVING PERSON
JUST LIKE
MISS IBUKI.
Gennai: OK.
[laughs]
THE ELECTRICAL CABLES
ARE FIXED.
HEY,
I FINISHED REPAIRING
THE ELECTRICAL CABLES.
HUH?
Gojiro:
THE WAY IT'S LOOKING,
WE'LL BE SWALLOWED UP
BY THE STORM.
ARE YOU SURE
WE'LL MAKE IT IN TIME?
I THINK SO,
THOUGH IT
IS A RACE
AGAINST NATURE.
GOOD GOD.
WE COULD BE
CONTAMINATED
ANY TIME NOW.
REMEMBER,
THIS IS FOR IBUKI.
SHE'S NEVER SEEN
THE OUTSIDE WORLD BEFORE.
[gasping]
AND NOW SHE'S
ABOUT TO GIVE BIRTH
TO A CHILD
IN THIS
GODFORSAKEN PLACE.
I WANT THAT CHILD
TO LIVE ITS LIFE
WITHOUT EVER NEEDING
A HAZMAT SUIT.
ACHIEVING THAT
WILL BE MY FINAL ACT
OF REPENTANCE
FOR MY MANY SINS.
GOJIRO, WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
LET'S CHECK HOW
THE CURRENT'S FLOWING.
OH, RIGHT,
ABSOLUTELY.
WE CAN USE
THIS MEASURING DEVICE.
IT'LL SIGNAL
WHETHER OR NOT
AN ELECTRICAL CURRENT
IS FLOWING.
HUH?
WELL, THAT'S ODD.
THIS ISN'T RIGHT
AT ALL.
I SWEAR I FIXED
THE CABLES
CORRECTLY.
THEN SOMETHING
AT THE SUBSTATION
HAS GONE WRONG.
WELL, GET OVER THERE
AND FIX IT AS QUICK
AS YOU CAN, GENNAI.
DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA HOW BIG
THE SUBSTATION IS?
IT'LL BE DIFFICULT
JUST FIGURING OUT
WHERE THE PROBLEM LIES.
NO, LET ME WORRY
ABOUT THE SUBSTATION.
WHAT?
THAT'S A KIND OFFER,
GOJIRO,
BUT ELECTRICAL REPAIRS
AREN'T SOMETHING
TO BE LEFT FOR AMATEURS
TO HANDLE.
I CAN DO IT.
AFTER ALL,
I USED TO WORK FOR
THE POWER COMPANY.
HUH? HEY, WAIT.
GOJIRO!
THE POWER COMPANY?
Kurobe: WAIT A MINUTE...
HEY,
WHERE'D YOU GO, AOI?
DAMN IT, HARUTO.
WE COMPLETELY
LOST HER.
THE WIND IS
PICKING UP.
Haruto:
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
IF THE WIND
GETS ANY STRONGER,
I DON'T THINK
THE CABLES'LL HOLD.
Soldier:
FOUND THEM!
Ibara: KANON. RUN!
Soldier: THEY'RE
MAKING A RUN FOR IT!
DON'T LET THEM
ESCAPE!
YOU, ACTIVATE
THAT THING.
YES, SIR.
WHAT THING?
[panting]
I MADE IT.
THIS MUST BE
THE SUBSTATION.
PLEASE HANG IN THERE,
IBUKI.
THIS SUCKS.
THEY TOTALLY
HAVE US
OUTGUNNED.
[explosion]
HUH?
HEY, IBARA,
SORRY WE'RE LATE!
THIS WAY!
GOOD WORK, AOI!
HURRY!
LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
[all gasp]
[heavy thudding]
WHAT'S THAT?
IT SOUNDS LIKE
IT'S REALLY HUGE.
[screams]
OH. [screams]
[gasps]
IT'S A GIANT
ROBOT SPIDER!
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Aoi: THE IRON SPIDER...
TOTAL DESTRUCTION...
AOI'S POWER...
THE TWO SIDES...
LIMITATIONS...
HELPLESSNESS,
THE BROKEN WHEEL...
THE PATH TO BELIEVE IN...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
AWAKENING.