[chirps]
NARUSE, THE WIND
IS ON ITS WAY.
["Angel" by angela playing]
[cawing]
[squawks]
WAIT. SO THE ZONE
IS SHIFTING,
AND IT'S HEADED
TOWARDS OUR LOCATION?
I'M AFRAID SO,
NARUSE.
THE WAY
IT'S MOVING NOW,
IT'LL EVENTUALLY
REACH THE PLANET.
AH, YOU CAN'T
BE SERIOUS!
HOW LONG
DO WE HAVE TILL IT
MAKES IT OUT HERE?
MAYBE THREE--
NO, TWO DAYS.
[groans]
THAT'S TOO SOON.
THE VICE PRINCIPAL'S
HELICOPTER WON'T
MAKE IT IN TIME.
IT'S CLEAR THE WIND IS
COMING FROM THE WEST.
LET'S CHECK OUT
WHAT IT'S LIKE
IN THE OTHER DIRECTIONS
RIGHT NOW.
[squeaking]
Gennai:
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
THE ANIMALS
ARE RUNNING AWAY
FROM THE EAST.
ARE YOU SURE
THE WIND'S NOT COMING
FROM OVER THERE?
THAT IS STRANGE.
THE WIND MUST HAVE
CHANGED DIRECTION.
HEAD BACK
TOWARDS THE WEST!
STILL,
THAT COULD BE BAD.
[counter beeping]
THERE IT IS.
IT'S COMING AT US.
LET'S GO, GENNAI!
IT'S AS THOUGH
THE WIND IS ALIVE.
IT'S CHASING US
ALL AROUND
THE STREETS.
Kurobe: SO ANYONE
HAVE ANY GOOD IDEAS?
THE ZONE HAS
COMPLETELY BLOCKED OFF
OUR WAY OUT
TO THE NORTH NOW, TOO.
IT SURE LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE RUN OUT
OF OPTIONS.
WE'RE TRAPPED
LIKE A BUNCH
OF HELPLESS RATS.
THEY'RE
GONNA DETONATE
THE SARCOPHAGUS
AND KILL EVERYONE.
HARUTO,
ISN'T THERE SOME WAY
WE CAN BREAK THROUGH
OR AROUND THE ZONE
TO GET OUT OF HERE?
CONTAMINANTS USUALLY
TEND TO SETTLE
ONTO THE GROUND.
IF WE COULD GET
AT LEAST 10 METERS
ABOVE THE GROUND
AND MOVE
AT 80 KILOMETERS
PER HOUR...
SO JUST FLAP OUR ARMS
AND FLY LIKE
A BUNCH OF BIRDS.
THAT'S SOME
GOOD THINKING THERE.
ACTUALLY, IT IS.
EXCUSE ME?
THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT CAN GET US
UP IN THE AIR HERE.
Kurobe: THE TRAIN.
[sighs]
I'M SO BORED.
WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH ME, ANYWAY?
I'M JUST
SITTING HERE,
DOING NOTHING,
AND WASTING
ALL MY TIME.
REALLY, IT'S NOT
THAT MUCH DIFFERENT
THAN MY DAYS
AT SCHOOL.
AS SOON AS SOMETHING
BAD HAPPENED TO ME,
I'D RUN AWAY AND
HIDE FROM EVERYBODY.
[chuckles]
[whimpers]
THIS SUCKS.
I WANT TO GO OUTSIDE.
Kurobe: OK,
IS EVERYBODY HERE?
Taeko: MISS IBUKI
IS ASLEEP.
THANKFULLY
HER CONTRACTIONS
HAVE EASED UP.
AND AOI'S
STILL HIDING
FROM THE WORLD.
Gojiro: SO WHAT WERE
YOU GOING TO TELL US?
MAKE IT QUICK.
MM.
WE'RE GOING TO DIVIDE
EVERYONE INTO TWO GROUPS.
WE GOT A LOT TO DO,
YOU GUYS,
SO PAY ATTENTION!
Gojiro: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY TWO GROUPS?
LISTEN UP.
AS EVERYONE CAN SEE,
THIS HERE
IS THE PLANET.
Gojiro:
WHAT'S THAT, A MAP?
No-sense:
RECOGNITION ERROR.
PLEASE REDRAW
THE IMAGE.
WILL YOU ALL JUST
SHUT UP AND LISTEN?!
ANYWAY, WE'RE GOING
TO FIX UP THE TRAIN
AND GET IT
RUNNING AGAIN.
AH.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
THE TRAIN'S
NEVER GOING TO WORK.
THAT THING'S
BEEN BROKEN
FOR SO LONG NOW.
WE KNOW IT'S BROKEN.
THAT'S WHY
WE'RE GONNA FIX IT.
HAVE YOU WORKED OUT
WHERE THE BREAK
POINTS ARE YET?
YEAH. THE ELECTRICAL CURRENT
IS FUNCTIONAL
UP TO THE SUBSTATION.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS,
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE THE WIND
HAS REACHED
THAT AREA YET.
MEANING THAT IT'S
SAFE FOR HUMANS.
SO GUESS WHO'S
REPAIRING IT,
GENNAI.
I FIGURED
I'D BE THE ONE.
THE TRAIN WILL
NEED SHIELDING
FROM THE CONTAMINATION.
I'LL HANDLE ALL
THE CONSTRUCTION
WORK.
YOU CAN
COUNT ON ME.
CONSTRUCTION AND
POWER LINE REPAIR?
I JUST HOPE THAT
THE FIRST DIVISION
DOESN'T SEE US.
SO, ANYWAY, THAT'S IT
FOR THE MAINTENANCE TEAM.
NOW LET'S GO OVER
THE DIVERSION TEAM'S TASKS.
A DIVERSION TEAM?
THE OZU SISTERS ARE
GOING TO WAKE UP SOON.
THIS TIME, THEY WILL BE
EVEN MORE DANGEROUS
AND WILL STOP AT NOTHING
TO HUNT US DOWN.
[murmurs]
HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THESE CHAINS?
[grunts]
AH, MAN.
MY UNIFORM'S
ALL SHREDDED UP.
[giggles]
WAIT JUST
A MINUTE.
IF THEY SEE YOU
OUT THERE,
THEY'LL
BLOW YOU AND
THE TRACKS UP.
UNDOUBTEDLY. THAT'S WHAT
THE DIVERSION TEAM IS FOR.
IT'LL DISTRACT
THE OZU SISTERS AND
THE FIRST DIVISION.
BUT OF COURSE
WE'LL NEED TO GET
THEIR ATTENTION FIRST.
WHAT IF THE OZU SISTERS
DON'T NOTICE
THE DIVERSION TEAM?
WE WON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
Shion: SIS. SIS.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
THAT YOU, SHION?
THANK GOODNESS, SIS.
YOU'RE OK!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
DEAD OR SOMETHING.
HEH. SO WHERE DID
THOSE BASTARDS GO?
I'M GONNA KILL
ALL OF 'EM.
[chuckles]
I CAN FEEL THEM.
Haruto: KANON OZU'S
SPECIAL POWER
ISN'T JUST LIMITED
TO ELECTRICAL DISCHARGE.
SHE CAN ALSO SENSE AND
LOCATE LIVING THINGS
BY THE IONS
IN THEIR BODIES.
SO THAT'S IT.
THAT'S HOW SHE KNEW
HOW TO FIND US
WHEN WE WERE HIDING
IN THE SUPERMARKET.
HOWEVER, SHE CAN ONLY
DETECT THESE IONS
WITHIN
A ONE-KILOMETER RADIUS,
WHICH MEANS, OF COURSE,
IF WE MOVE IN
NEAR THE OZU SISTERS
SOMEWHERE
INSIDE OF THAT RADIUS,
WE'LL BE ABLE
TO DRAW THEM OUT
INTO OUR DIRECTION.
HEH.
[birds chirping]
GRANNY AYAME.
WHY, DR. EDOGAWA.
WHAT BRINGS YOU
OUT HERE TO SEE
THIS OLD LADY?
[sighs]
I WANTED TO ASK YOU
WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN STARING AT.
COULD IT BE
THAT NURSERY
OVER THERE?
[children talking,
yelling]
I'LL GET
MY THINGS TOGETHER
AND LEAVE HERE
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
[sighs] NO MATTER HOW LONG
I SIT AROUND WAITING,
NO ONE'S GOING
TO COME GET ME, ANYWAY.
[groans]
IT IS NEVER
AN EASY JOB
TRYING
TO SAVE LIVES.
Kurobe:
PAY ATTENTION,
EVERYBODY!
TO MAKE
THIS PLAN WORK,
WE'RE GOING
TO NEED TO BE
THOROUGHLY PREPARED.
MAINTENANCE TEAM,
MAKE SURE YOU BRING
THE COILS, LADDERS,
AND TOOLS YOU'LL NEED
TO RIG THE POWER CABLES.
DIVERSION TEAM,
PACK UP THE WEAPONS.
LOAD EVERY GUN
AND EXPLOSIVE WE HAVE
INTO THE TRUCK.
[Gennai grunts]
HMM?
THIS IS ALL
THE CABLING?
THERE'S NO WAY
THAT THIS
IS ENOUGH
TO REACH
ALL THE WAY TO
THE SUBSTATION.
YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
A DIFFERENT PLAN.
WE'RE GOING TO USE
WHAT WE HAVE
TO APPLY
THE HIGH VOLTAGE
TO THE TRACKS,
WHICH'LL BE FASTER
AND GIVE MORE POWER.
WAIT. DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
ALL THE DOWNTOWN TRAINS
USE A D.C. SYSTEM!
HUH?
EH?
IN ORDER TO REDUCE
THE RISKS
OF HIGH VOLTAGE,
TRANSFORMERS
AT THE SUBSTATION
CONVERT THE POWER
DOWN TO A 1,500-VOLTS
D.C. SETUP!
OTHERWISE, THE MOTORS
IN THE TRAINS
WOULD BURN UP!
Kurobe: GOJIRO...
YOU SEEM TO KNOW A LOT
ABOUT ELECTRICAL STUFF.
WHAT SORT OF WORK
DID YOU DO BEFORE
THE ACCIDENT?
EH, THAT'S
IN THE PAST.
IT DOESN'T
MATTER ANYMORE.
I THINK I'LL GO
CHECK ON IBUKI.
HMM?
[sighs]
TODAY'S THE LAST DAY
I'LL BE ABLE TO LOOK
UP AT THE SKY, ISN'T IT?
EVEN THOUGH I KNOW
IT'S ALL ARTIFICIAL,
THE IMPACT IS REAL.
MAYBE SINCE IT'S
MY LAST TIME SEEING IT,
I THINK IT LOOKS
MORE BEAUTIFUL THAN EVER.
I KNOW THAT FEELING
VERY WELL.
THE SAME THING
HAPPENED TO ME
ON THE DAY OF OUR
SEND-OFF CEREMONY.
UP TO THAT POINT,
I HAD BEEN DYING TO GET
OUT OF THAT PLACE.
EVEN SO,
I FOUND MYSELF CRYING
BY THE SCHOOL GATE,
WATCHING THE SUN
GO DOWN.
I FELT LIKE THERE
WAS A NEW WORLD
WAITING FOR ME
OUTSIDE THOSE GATES.
I GUESS I WAS
JUST AFRAID TO TAKE
THAT FIRST STEP.
A NEW WORLD, HUH?
TOMORROW
I'M GOING TO TAKE
A FIRST STEP
LIKE THAT, TOO.
AREN'T YOU AFRAID?
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'LL BE SCARY FOR YOU?
MM-MMM.
NOT AT ALL.
THIS CHILD
IS MY STRENGTH.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
I WON'T GIVE UP.
I'LL BE BRAVE.
[gasping]
IT HURTS.
ARE YOU HAVING
CONTRACTIONS?
W-WHAT SHOULD I DO?
IBUKI!
MR. GOJIRO,
PLEASE DO SOMETHING.
YOU WANT ME
TO DO SOMETHING?
AREN'T YOU THE ONE
ON THE RESCUE TEAM?
[gasps]
COME ON, PLEASE.
WHEN SHE
GOES INTO LABOR,
YOU HAVE TO DELIVER
THE BABY.
BUT I CAN'T DO IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
[footsteps]
HUH?
[panting]
TAEKO, IS THAT YOU?
TAEKO, IS MISS IBUKI
GOING INTO LABOR?
ARE YOU GONNA
DELIVER THE BABY?
IF SO, I KNOW
YOU'LL DO GREAT.
UNLIKE ME,
YOU'RE SUPER SMART.
YOU CAN
HANDLE ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME!
[gasps]
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
IT'S JUST...
I'M AFRAID OF TOUCHING
A HUMAN LIFE.
I'M SCARED
I MIGHT BREAK IT
WITH THESE HANDS.
IBUKI'S HAVING
LABOR PAINS AGAIN?
SO WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO NOW?
I'LL CONTACT
THE HOSPITAL
IN NAGOYA.
A DOCTOR THERE CAN
TALK ME THROUGH IT,
AND I'LL DELIVER
THE BABY MYSELF.
HOLD ON JUST A MINUTE.
YOU'RE THE STAR
OF THE DIVERSION TEAM.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
THIS REQUIRES
MEDICAL EXPERTISE.
IF ONLY OUR HEAD NURSE
WAS STILL HERE.
HUH?
SEE, SHE USED TO BE
THE HEAD MATERNITY NURSE
IN THE OLD CAPITAL.
YEAH, THAT OLD LADY.
IF YOU GIRLS HADN'T
EVACUATED HER,
SHE COULD
HAVE DELIVERED
THE BABY FOR US.
HUH?
Dr. Edogawa:
GRANNY AYAME!
[grumbles]
[panting]
YOU CAN GO PUT
YOUR THINGS BACK, GRANNY.
WE ARE IN NEED
OF YOUR HELP.
[radio whines]
Ayame: HELLO.
CAN ANYONE HEAR ME?
WHO IS THIS?
IT'S GRANNY AYAME,
THE LADY
YOU GIRLS RESCUED.
I HEARD YOU'RE
HAVING CHILDBIRTH
ISSUES OVER THERE.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TALK YOU
THROUGH IT.
BUT I CAN'T DO IT.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE AFRAID,
AREN'T YOU?
I DON'T BLAME YOU.
EVERYONE
GETS NERVOUS
WHEN TAKING
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR HANDLING
A HUMAN LIFE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
AND I'M SAYING THIS
AS SOMEONE
WHO'S DELIVERED
HUNDREDS OF BABIES.
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL THING
YOU CAN DO
IN THIS WORLD.
I'LL TALK YOU
THROUGH IT,
AND WE'LL DO
OUR BEST TOGETHER.
Ibuki: TAEKO.
MISS IBUKI.
WE NEED YOU.
THIS CHILD
NEEDS YOUR HELP.
Ibuki: PLEASE.
OK.
SO HERE IT IS.
THIS IS THE SHELTER
THAT WE'LL BE TOWING
WITH THE TRAIN.
WE'LL SET UP IBUKI
INSIDE OF HERE
JUST IN CASE
SHE GOES INTO LABOR
TOMORROW.
Kurobe: HEY,
CARRY THAT SIDE,
WILL YOU?
Gojiro: IT WEIGHS A TON.
WHAT IS THIS, LEAD?
Gennai: WE COULD
SURE USE SOME HELP.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
SOMETHING REALLY BIG
IS HAPPENING
OUT THERE.
MAYBE I--NO!
I DON'T WANT TO GET
IN EVERYONE'S WAY
MORE THAN
I ALREADY HAVE!
No-sense:
MISS GOOD-FOR-NOTHING AOI.
AW, NOW YOU'RE
BEING MEAN TO ME,
TOO, NO-SENSE!
THEY WILL
PUT THEIR PLAN
INTO MOTION
EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING.
THEY HAVE A PLAN?
[components rattling]
HARUTO.
NARUSE. HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU LOOK GROUCHY.
I'M NOT.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
IF YOU'RE
REALLY ON OUR SIDE.
WE NEED TO GET THAT
OUT IN THE OPEN
RIGHT NOW.
HONESTLY, I'M NOT SURE
ABOUT IT MYSELF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'D GO THIS FAR
TO SAVE THOSE HUMANS.
WHAT GOOD
DOES IT DO FOR US?
IF I HAD TO GIVE A REASON
WHY I'M HELPING YOU
DESPITE MY FEELINGS,
WELL, I GUESS IT'D BE
BECAUSE I WANT TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH HUMANS,
UNDERSTANDING THEM.
Ibara: WOW. LOOK AT ALL
THE STARS IN THE SKY.
ARE THESE
ALL PROJECTIONS?
Kurobe: WOULD YOU
LOOK AT THIS?
YOU PULLED OUT ALL
THE STOPS TONIGHT,
HAVEN'T YOU,
NO-SENSE?
I ASKED HIM
TO DO THIS
FOR US, FOREMAN.
Ibuki:
AFTER ALL, THIS IS
OUR LAST DINNER PARTY
AT THE PLANET.
YOU'RE RIGHT, IBUKI.
OK, THEN. LET'S EAT UP
AS MUCH AS WE CAN
SO WE'RE READY
FOR TOMORROW!
ALL RIGHT,
NOW YOU'RE TALKING!
[laughter]
WOW. THESE RICE BALLS
ARE DELICIOUS.
SURE ARE.
HUH?
HMM?
[groans]
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S
SO MUCH EASIER
TO GET NUTRITION
THIS WAY.
DON'T BE LIKE THAT
WITHOUT TRYING
SOMETHING FIRST.
IT'S DELICIOUS,
I PROMISE.
NO, THANKS.
HUMAN FOOD'S
NOT REALLY MY THING.
WHAT'D YOU SAY,
YOU COCKY LITTLE
BASTARD?
THAT'S IT.
HOLD
THE KID DOWN!
GIVE HIM
A TASTE OF SOME
HUMAN FOOD.
STOP IT! STOP IT!
LET ME DOWN!
YEAH. THAT'LL
TEACH YOU.
COME ON AND EAT.
IT'LL MAKE YOU
BIG AND STRONG,
PREPPY.
[laughs]
I MISS AOI.
I WISH SHE
WOULD COME JOIN US
FOR DINNER.
Taeko: ME, TOO.
YOU KNOW
SHE'D LOVE THE FOOD.
[grumbles]
HMM.
EH?
THIS ISN'T SO BAD.
[laughs]
YOU SEE THERE?
ISN'T HAVING
A MEAL TOGETHER
WORTH IT
AND TASTY, TOO?
Aoi:
THOSE RICE BALLS...
I WAS THE ONE
WHO MADE THEM.
DID YOU THINK
THEY WERE OK?
[gasps]
THEY WERE DELICIOUS,
OF COURSE.
NO KIDDING.
ANYONE CAN MAKE
SIMPLE RICE BALLS,
AND THEY'LL TASTE
JUST FINE--
[grunts]
COME ON, AOI.
YOU SHOULD
SIT DOWN
AND JOIN US.
[crying]
IBARA!
[grunts]
[laughter]
Aoi: I MISSED YOU.
[radio whines]
Ayame:
ARE THE CONTRACTIONS
GETTING CLOSER TOGETHER?
YEAH. THEY'RE
AROUND 10 MINUTES
APART NOW.
[snoring]
HER WATER'LL BREAK SOON,
SO BE READY FOR THAT.
MOVE HER
INTO THE DELIVERY ROOM
BEFORE THEN.
ALL RIGHT, NARUSE,
HERE'S HOW OUR PLAN
IS GOING TO GO
MOVING FORWARD.
AFTER THE TRAIN
MAKES ITS DESTINATION--
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
THE HELICOPTER
WILL SHOW UP THERE
TO RESCUE US, RIGHT?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A PERFECT PLAN TO ME.
Ibuki: WAIT.
HUH?
MISS IBUKI,
WHAT IS IT?
I NEED YOU TO...
SAVE ONE MORE PERSON
FOR ME.
HUH?
[neighs]
YOU GOTTA GET IN THERE.
COME ON. GET IN.
SAY, MR. GENNAI...
EH?
ARE YOU REALLY
TRYING TO TAKE
ALL THESE ANIMALS
WITH US, TOO?
YOU BETCHA.
IF I LEAVE THEM
HERE AT THE PLANET,
THEY'LL BE SWALLOWED UP
BY THE ZONE,
AND THEY'LL ALL DIE,
SO I ASKED KUROBE
TO BUILD A SHELTER
FOR ALL THE ANIMALS
TO USE AS WELL.
OH. THERE ARE SO MANY.
THAT'S COOL.
IT'S LIKE...
HMM?
IT'S LIKE
THE STORY
OF NOAH'S ARK.
NOAH'S FAMILY
GATHERED UP
ALL THE ANIMALS
TWO BY TWO
AND PUT THEM
IN THE ARK HE BUILT.
THEY BECAME
THE GUARDIANS
OF THE NEW WORLD.
WOW. GUARDIANS
OF THE NEW WORLD?
YES, THOUGH ONLY
LIVING CREATURES
ARE ALLOWED
IN THAT ARRANGEMENT.
HUH?
ROBOTS MUST REMAIN
IN THE WORLD THAT
WILL BE DESTROYED.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DID THEY REALLY SAY
THAT THEY'RE JUST GOING
TO LEAVE YOU BEHIND
ALL ALONE?
THAT'S AWFUL, NO-SENSE.
I WON'T LET THEM DO THAT.
COME WITH US!
IF I JOINED YOU
ON YOUR MISSION,
I WOULD ONLY SERVE
TO SLOW YOU DOWN.
I AM A GUIDE ROBOT
DESIGNED TO EXIST
AT THE PLANET.
MY PURPOSE
HAS COME TO AN END.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
YOU'RE A LIVING BEING
WITH A GENTLE HEART!
Ibara: A FIRST DIVISION
SOLDIER?
JUST HANG ON
A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SAYING THIS PERSON
YOU WANT US TO SAVE
IS A MEMBER
OF THE FIRST DIVISION?
[pants]
YES.
HE'S NOT
A BAD PERSON.
I'M SURE HE'S STILL
SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
PLEASE, YOU HAVE
TO SAVE HIM.
YOU'RE REALLY
ASKING A LOT OF US,
YOU KNOW.
WHY IS HE
SO IMPORTANT TO YOU?
BECAUSE HE'S
THIS CHILD'S FATHER.
WHAT?
[gasps]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I MAY HAVE MET
THIS GUY.
WHERE?!
AT THE WATER
TREATMENT FACILITY.
WHEN I WAS
BEING HELD,
ONE OF THE SOLDIERS
HELPED ME ESCAPE.
THAT'S EXACTLY
SOMETHING HE'D DO.
PLEASE, WILL YOU
FIND HIM FOR ME?
WELL, HE DID
HELP AOI OUT.
I GUESS IT WOULD BE
A GOOD THING
TO REPAY HIM.
Kurobe: OK,
THE MAINTENANCE TEAM
IS READY TO MOVE OUT.
Ibara: ROGER.
LET'S DO A FINAL
HEAD COUNT.
Kurobe: 1, 2, 3--
HUH? WHERE'D GENNAI GO?
I'M GONNA MISS YOU,
NO-SENSE.
GOODBYE.
[engine grinding]
HUH?
[gasps]
I AM SORRY TO KEEP YOU
WAITING, MISS AOI.
[squeals]
THAT'S NOT NO-SENSE,
IS IT?
THIS IS SO COOL!
YOU'RE
A ROBOT SOLDIER!
I'M HAPPY
YOU'RE PLEASED.
I GATHERED UP
WHAT I COULD FIND
TO GIVE HIM THIS
LITTLE MAKEOVER.
YOU'RE AWESOME,
MR. GENNAI. THANK YOU!
I FIGURED THIS
WOULD HELP HIM
BE OF GOOD USE
TO US.
SO THIS IS
THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
YES, IT IS,
NO-SENSE.
HOW DO YOU
LIKE IT?
THE BREEZE. THE BREEZE
OUTSIDE FEELS VERY WARM.
[groans]
MORNING, SIS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
THE ENEMY IS
MAKING THEIR MOVE,
SO LET'S GET GOING.
[radio whines]
NARUSE, REPORT.
COME IN. NARUSE.
[yawns]
DAMN IT.
SHE'S NOT
RESPONDING.
IT'S 6:30
IN THE MORNING.
THEY MIGHT STILL
BE ASLEEP, VICE PRINCIPAL.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
LET THEM REST
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER, SIR.
I COULDN'T MAKE CONTACT
WITH THEM AT ALL
LAST NIGHT EITHER.
HEY, CHANNEL TWO!
Ayame: SHUT UP!
WE HEARD YOU
THE FIRST TIME!
WE'RE A LITTLE BUSY
RIGHT NOW PREPPING
TO DELIVER A BABY.
THIS IS GRANNY AYAME
FROM NAGOYA.
I'M TAKING OVER
THIS CHANNEL FOR NOW.
DID SHE SAY, "BABY"?
THERE'S THAT
PREGNANT WOMAN.
I GUESS SHE'S
ON THE VERGE
OF GIVING BIRTH.
[cell phone buzzes]
HMM.
VICE PRINCIPAL MISHIMA,
I NEED YOU TO TAKE
IMMEDIATE ACTION.
CALM DOWN,
MUSHANOKOJI.
AND JUST HOW DO YOU
EXPECT ME TO CALM DOWN?
SOME UNIDENTIFIED,
PROBABLY CRAZY PERSON
IS SENDING ME
STRANGE MESSAGES
FROM THE OLD CAPITAL
USING MY SATELLITE
COMMUNICATION SYSTEM.
THAT'S JUST NARUSE.
I GAVE HER ACCESS
TO YOUR LINE TO USE
IN AN EMERGENCY.
WHAT DID SHE SAY
IN THE MESSAGES?
BUT, VICE PRINCIPAL,
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
MY OWN PRIVATE LINE.
WHY WOULD SHE BE
TRYING TO CONTACT US
USING THAT FATSO'S LINE,
ANYWAY?
THE RADIOS
ARE STILL WORKING.
WHY DIDN'T SHE USE HERS?
SHE PROBABLY
HAS A GOOD REASON
FOR NOT USING IT.
WHATEVER IT IS,
SOMETHING'S
HAPPENING
IN THE OLD CAPITAL.
OH, HERE WE GO.
THE VICE PRINCIPAL
REPLIED.
SO WHAT'S WITH
THE COMPUTER?
WHY ARE YOU SENDING
E-MAIL MESSAGES?
WHY NOT USE THE RADIO
LIKE NORMAL?
WE CAN'T.
THE OZU SISTERS
USE THE SAME
RADIO CHANNELS
THAT WE DO.
THEY'D HEAR
EVERYTHING WE'D SAY.
[shrieks]
OZU SISTERS.
AOI, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?
NARUSE,
THE DIVERSION TEAM IS READY.
WE CAN HEAD OUT ANYTIME.
LET'S GO AHEAD
AND PUT OUR PLAN
INTO MOTION NOW.
GO GET 'EM,
DIVERSION TEAM!
GOOD LUCK, NO-SENSE!
BE CAREFUL OUT THERE!
[gasping]
OZU...SISTERS.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[grunts]
HEH.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Kanon: THE OUTSIDE WORLD...
TIME LIMIT IS AT SUNSET...
REINSTATEMENT...
FREE WILL...
THE HISTORY OF MANKIND...
THEIR SELF-DESTRUCTION...
LIFE...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
HUMAN.