[chimes ringing]
Woman: RISE.
[chairs clatter]
Woman: BOW.
BE SEATED.
[chairs clatter]
GOOD MORNING, CLASS.
THE TIME HAS ARRIVED.
TOMORROW, YOU'LL BEGIN
YOUR FIELD SERVICE.
REMAIN SEATED
FOR THE FINAL ROLL CALL
OF THE PROGRAM.
[gasps]
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
Aoi: I'VE BEEN THINKING,
DOESN'T THIS PLACE
KIND OF REMIND YOU GUYS
OF OUR OLD SCHOOL?
I WANNA GO HOME
ALREADY.
TIME TO GO, GIRLS.
[whimpers]
[groans]
Ibara: LET'S GO!
["Angel" by angela playing]
Ibara:
"JASA HEADQUARTERS."
I WONDER
WHAT "JASA" MEANS.
DON'T KNOW.
NEVER HEARD OF IT.
I THINK I'VE
HEARD OF IT BEFORE.
IT'S A NATIONAL
SPACE EXPLORATION
ORGANIZATION.
OH. THAT MEANS
THERE'S PROBABLY A LOT
OF EQUIPMENT AVAILABLE.
IT COULD BE USEFUL
FOR THOSE LIVING THERE.
OK, LET'S GET GOING.
[rotors whirring]
Mishima:
WE'RE SENDING IN
CHOPPERS
THAT ARE CARRYING
SPECIAL CONTAINERS
FROM TRISTAR INDUSTRIES.
THEY'LL BE
USED TO STORE
THE HIGH-LEVEL WASTE
THE THREE OF YOU
DISCOVERED.
IT'S THE BEST SOLUTION
FOR THE TIME BEING.
I COPY THAT, SIR.
WE CAN SEE THEM NOW.
Mishima:
THEY'LL REMAIN THERE
UNTIL WE CAN ARRANGE
PROPER DISPOSAL.
AT LEAST FOR NOW,
YOU WON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ANY WASTE LEAKING.
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF SOMETHING ELSE NOW.
IN THE MEANTIME...
[yawns]
KEEP SEARCHING
FOR SURVIVORS.
Ibara: ROGER.
HOW'S THE PROFESSOR?
IS HE HOLDING UP OK?
HE'S DOING BETTER,
JUDGING BY
HIS TEST RESULTS.
NARUSE...
YES, VICE PRINCIPAL?
THANK YOU FOR SAVING
PROFESSOR SHIBA.
I MAY HAVE BEEN
WRONG ABOUT HIM.
COPY THAT.
NARUSE OUT.
Pilot: HIGH-LEVEL WASTE
CONTAINMENT COMPLETED.
YOU SURE IT'S OK
TO SET THEM DOWN
IN THE MIDDLE
OF AN INTERSECTION?
NOBODY COMES
THROUGH HERE ANYWAY.
COME ON.
LET'S HEAD BACK.
HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
[cannon booms]
[panting]
LOOK AT
THESE TRACKS.
I WONDER WHAT
THEY'RE FROM.
IBARA,
OVER THERE!
HELLO!
ANYONE THERE?
[gasping]
SIR, DON'T MOVE.
I'M GONNA TRY
TO GET YOU OUT.
GET MY DAUGHTER FIRST.
SHE'S IN THE BACK.
ALL RIGHT. I'M ON IT.
[girls gasp]
Ibara: SHE'S...
PREGNANT.
WE HAVE
TO GET HER
OUT OF THERE.
HELP ME OUT.
[radio whines]
Mishima:
NARUSE, COME IN.
I'M HERE, SIR.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
I JUST RECEIVED WORD
ONE OF OUR CHOPPERS
WAS SHOT DOWN.
[gasps]
WHOEVER DID IT
APPARENTLY STOLE
ALL THE HIGH-LEVEL WASTE
CONTAINERS AS WELL.
SOMEBODY STOLE IT?
WHY WOULD ANYBODY
TAKE THAT WASTE?
THAT'S WHAT I NEED
YOU TO FIND OUT.
HOLD ON. WHAT'S
THE VICE PRINCIPAL
TALKING ABOUT?
Woman:
THEY'RE COMING.
[pained]
THE GHOSTS...
OF THE SELF-DEFENSE
FORCE.
SELF-DEFENSE FORCE?
WHAT GHOSTS?
[rumbling]
[girls gasp]
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?!
Woman: IT'S THEM...
THE FIRST DIVISION.
Aoi: WHAT DO YOU
MEAN BY GHOSTS OF
THE SELF-DEFENSE FORCE?
THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO ATTACKED US.
THEY DID THIS.
THAT SMOKE
SHOULD HOLD THEM.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
THE AMBULANCE
WILL BLOCK THEIR FIRE!
MOVE IT!
[grunting]
[man yells]
SORRY.
THERE THEY ARE.
OPEN FIRE.
SEE YA.
WAS THAT THE MINISTRY
OF DEFENSE'S LATEST LAND MINE?
THEY'VE MADE
SOME IMPROVEMENTS.
[Aoi panting]
CAN SOMEONE
PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
WHO WERE THOSE GUYS,
ANYWAY?!
Man: THEY BELONG TO
THE FIRST DIVISION.
THEY SHOW UP
IN THE CITY
FROM TIME TO TIME,
BUT THAT'S
THE FIRST TIME
THEY'VE EVER
TRIED TO ATTACK US.
WHY WOULD THEY
WANT TO HARM US?
DO YOU THINK YOUR BABY'S
GOING TO BE OK?
YEAH. THANKS FOR
SAVING US BACK THERE.
I'M IBUKI KAJII.
THIS HERE IS
MY FATHER GOJIRO.
YOU'RE COPPELION, RIGHT?
I HEARD
YOUR CONVERSATION
YESTERDAY
ON A RADIO THAT
PROFESSOR SHIBA GAVE ME.
[giggles]
NICE TO MEET
YOU THREE.
Mishima: WHAT?
THE FIRST DIVISION?
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAW?
YES, SIR!
THAT IS
WHAT WE SAW!
IT'S INSANE!
YOU'VE GOT
TO GET US OUT!
THE FIRST DIVISION.
Ibuse: IT SEEMS STRANGE.
I MEAN, WEREN'T THEY--
SUPPOSEDLY WIPED OUT?
YES.
IMMEDIATELY
AFTER THE ACCIDENT,
THE MASS
EXODUS OF PEOPLE
PARALYZED TRAFFIC.
THOSE THAT WERE STUCK
ON THE ROADS AND BRIDGES
SUCCUMBED TO
THE CONTAMINATION.
SOME CHOSE
TO REMAIN BEHIND,
SEEKING SHELTER
IN THE CITY'S
SAFE ZONES,
WAITING FOR
THE GOVERNMENT
TO RESCUE THEM.
BUT WAIT AS THEY MIGHT,
NO ONE CAME
TO THEIR RESCUE.
THAT'S BECAUSE
THE SELF-DEFENSE FORCE
SENT TO RESCUE THEM
ALSO SUFFERED
MANY CASUALTIES.
OH, AND SO THAT WAS
THE FIRST DIVISION.
CORRECT. THEY WERE
THE FIRST FORCE SENT
INTO THE CITY.
THE GOVERNMENT FELT
IT WAS TOO DANGEROUS
TO SEND MORE IN.
THEY CANCELED
THE OPERATION.
THE RESCUE ATTEMPTS
CEASED,
AND THE OLD CAPITAL
WAS SEALED INSIDE
A HIGH LEAD WALL.
Ibara:
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN DO YOU THINK
THE FIRST DIVISION
IS ATTACKING US
OUT OF REVENGE?
IT'S A POSSIBILITY,
SO YOU NEED
TO BE CAREFUL,
AND I WILL SEND IN
A HELICOPTER.
WILL DO, SIR.
JUST HURRY UP, OK?!
PLEASE COME GET US
SO WE CAN
GET OUT OF HERE!
MR. KAJII, DO YOU
HAPPEN TO KNOW
OF A PLACE CALLED
JASA HEADQUARTERS?
YES. THAT'S WHERE
WE ALL LIVE.
IBARA, OVER THERE.
DAMN. THOSE GHOSTS
DON'T GIVE UP
EASILY, DO THEY?
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
SNEAK OUR WAY OUT.
AOI,
KEEP ABSOLUTELY QUIET.
[gasps]
[soft grunting]
[groans]
MM-MMM. MM-MMM.
[soft grunting]
Gojiro: OH, NO.
SHE'S HAVING
CONTRACTIONS
AGAIN.
Taeko: OH, NO.
THERE THEY ARE!
[girls gasp]
WE'VE BEEN SPOTTED.
LET'S GO.
TAKE 'EM OUT!
DAMN IT.
LOOKS LIKE YOU NEED
A LITTLE BIT OF HELP
THERE, EH, IBUKI?
MAYBE A LITTLE.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
HE'S
ONE OF US.
PICK UP THE PACE, FOLKS.
THE GHOSTS
MEAN BUSINESS.
EVERYONE GET
IN THE ARMORED VEHICLE!
HEH HEH HEH.
[yelling]
TAKE THIS!
[laughs]
I'LL WASH YOU
ALL THE WAY
TO THE OCEAN!
[laughs]
HOW DO YOU
LIKE ME NOW?!
[laughs]
HURRY UP!
CAN YOU WALK?
YEAH.
TAEKO, BEHIND YOU!
[gasps]
[machine gun fires]
PICK IT UP.
I'M ALMOST OUT OF WATER.
HURRY! GET IN!
Taeko:
WE'RE IN.
EVERYBODY'S
INSIDE NOW!
STEP ON IT, GENNAI!
YOU GOT IT!
[panting]
OH, MAN.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
THEY HAD GUNS,
AND THEY WERE
SHOOTING AT ME.
AOI'S TAKING IT HARD.
THAT WAS INSANE...
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
[gasps]
[gasping]
TAEKO!
Ibuse:
VICE PRINCIPAL,
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE SELF-DEFENSE
FORCE, RIGHT?
THEN HOW DID WE
GET ROPED INTO
A SECURITY DETAIL?
AREN'T THERE GUARDS
FOR THIS SORT
OF THING?
IT'S THE PRIME MINISTER'S
ORDERS.
Man: AH!
THERE YOU ARE,
MISHIMA. [chuckles]
THANKS FOR ALL
YOUR HARD WORK.
I CAME ALL THIS WAY
JUST TO SEE YOU.
PRIME MINISTER
I ASSURE YOU
WE MAINTAIN
EXTREMELY CLEAN
AIR HERE.
YOU DON'T
NEED TO WEAR
THAT MASK.
THIS CITY IS RATHER CLOSE
TO THE CONTAMINATED ZONE.
THERE'S ALWAYS
THE POSSIBILITY.
CONTAMINATION'S
NOT A PROBLEM HERE.
A MASK ALONE
DOESN'T HELP ANYWAY.
YOU HAVE TO WEAR
A FULL SUIT.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
LET'S TALK
INSIDE MY LIMOUSINE.
Ibuse: GUESS
HE'S NOT GOING
TO TAKE
THAT THING OFF,
IS HE?
THE PRIME MINISTER
IS IGNORANT,
NOT UNLIKE MOST
OF HIS CONSTITUENCY.
Prime Minister:
THANK YOU FOR
TAKING THE RISK
TO BROADCAST
THAT VIDEO
THE OTHER DAY.
THE INTERNATIONAL
CONFERENCE IS
BEGINNING TOMORROW.
THERE WILL BE
LEADERS FROM ALL
AROUND THE WORLD
MEETING
IN THE NEW CAPITAL.
IT'S A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY.
THE WORLD
WILL COME TOGETHER
TO GAIN A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING
OF ENVIRONMENTAL
POLLUTION.
SO, VICE PRINCIPAL MISHIMA,
HOW ARE THOSE DOLLS
OF OURS PERFORMING?
THE DOLLS?
OH, YEAH.
I'VE HEARD OF THEM.
THEY'RE CALLED
COPPER ION OR
SOMETHING, RIGHT?
IT'S COPPELION, SIR.
Ibara: VICE PRINCIPAL,
I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
TAEKO'S BEEN SHOT.
PARDON, SIR.
IS SHE IN ANY DANGER
OF DYING?
NO, SIR.
SHE'LL SURVIVE,
BUT EVEN WITH
OUR REGENERATIVE
ABILITIES,
SHE'LL NEED AT LEAST
A WEEK OF BED REST.
I DON'T THINK
WE'LL BE ABLE
TO EVADE THE GHOSTS
THAT LONG.
ARE YOU REFERRING
TO THE FIRST DIVISION?
[crash]
[gasping]
D-DID YOU SAY,
"THE FIRST DIVISION"?
Ibara:
VICE PRINCIPAL,
WE REALLY
NEED YOU TO SEND
THAT HELICOPTER
TO HELP GET TAEKO
AND THE PREGNANT
LADY TO SAFETY.
ME, TOO! ME, TOO!
IT'LL BE THERE A.S.A.--
Prime Minister: WAIT!
ELIMINATING THE ENEMY
IS THE FIRST PRIORITY.
WHO IS THAT,
AND WHAT DOES HE MEAN?
HE OBVIOUSLY
DOESN'T KNOW
WE'RE A RESCUE UNIT
AND NOT
A FIGHTING UNIT.
[groans] I AM
PRIME MINISTER NATSUME!
YOU'RE MY SUBORDINATE,
AND YOU'LL DO AS I SAY!
YOU ARE NOW OFFICIALLY
A FIGHTING UNIT.
YOU HEAR ME?!
BUT, SIR, THEY'RE
NOT EQUIPPED FOR
THAT ASSIGNMENT.
Ibara: I DON'T CARE IF
YOU'RE THE PRIME MINISTER!
WE'RE HERE
FOR RESCUE MISSIONS, IDIOT!
WHAT?!
YOU INSOLENT GIRL!
THERE ARE
A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE
WHO NEED OUR HELP.
NOW LISTEN HERE,
YOU STUPID CHILD!
I AM THE MOST
IMPORTANT MAN
IN JAPAN,
AND MY ORDER
IS FINAL!
[gasps]
WIPE OUT
THE FIRST DIVISION!
AND I'M NOT SENDING
A SINGLE HELICOPTER
UNTIL YOU DO!
JUST A MINUTE,
PRIME MINISTER!
YOU LISTEN TO ME!
YOU THERE,
PRIME MINISTER?
NO! IBARA,
WHY'D YOU YELL AT HIM
LIKE THAT?!
MM, I MIGHT
HAVE OVERREACTED.
I'M SORRY, AOI.
YOU'RE SCREAMING
LIKE LITTLE BABIES
BACK THERE.
QUIET DOWN NOW,
AND ACT YOUR AGE!
[whimpers]
WHY'S HE YELLING?
WHAT DID I DO?
HE'S LIKE THAT
TO EVERYONE.
HE IS OUR LEADER,
FOREMAN KUROBE.
A FOREMAN?
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND I'M GENNAI,
THE HANDYMAN.
I'M PLEASED
TO MEET YOU.
YOU, TOO.
WE'RE THE UNIT--
OH, WE KNOW.
YOU'RE THAT SPECIAL
UNIT THEY CALL
COPPELION, RIGHT?
YOU CAME
DOWN HERE TO RESCUE
FOLKS LIKE US.
WELL, WE'RE TRYING
TO HELP OUT.
[sighs]
BUT I'M SORRY.
WE CAN'T DO THAT
WITHOUT A HELICOPTER.
HEY, FOREMAN,
I'M WORRIED ABOUT
MY DAUGHTER'S CONDITION.
TAKE US BACK
TO JASA HEADQUARTERS
SO SHE CAN GET
SOME REST.
THIS IS WHY
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO GO WALKING
OUTSIDE ON YOUR OWN.
WE'VE ALL SEEN
THAT THE GHOSTS
HAVE BEEN ACTING
STRANGE LATELY.
BUT IBUKI
IS NEARLY
FULL-TERM NOW.
SHE COULD
GO INTO LABOR
AT JUST ABOUT
ANY TIME.
Kurobe:
I'M WELL AWARE OF THAT.
NOW LET'S GET THE HELL
BACK TO OUR HIDEOUT.
Mishima:
PRIME MINISTER
NATSUME,
PLEASE RECONSIDER
YOUR ORDER
TO NARUSE.
WE SHOULD
AT LEAST GO RESCUE
THE PREGNANT WOMAN.
CHIEF CABINET
SECRETARY...
Secretary: RIGHT NOW,
NOTHING YOU SAY WILL
GET THROUGH TO HIM.
Mishima:
THE PRIME MINISTER
TURNED PALE
THE MOMENT
I MENTIONED
THE FIRST DIVISION.
DOES THAT HAVE
SOMETHING TO DO
WITH WHY HE
WON'T RESPOND?
I'M A VERY BUSY MAN,
VICE PRINCIPAL.
I'M SORRY,
BUT THE CONFERENCE
IS MY PRIORITY
RIGHT NOW.
IT SHOULDN'T
BE A PROBLEM
TO HAVE THE DOLLS
HANG IN A LITTLE LONGER,
CONSIDERING THE MONEY
WE SPENT CREATING THEM.
Ibuse: THAT BONY
OLD BASTARD!
I'VE KNOWN OUGAI
A LONG TIME.
HE CAN BE HARD
TO DEAL WITH,
BUT WITHOUT HIM,
ALL OF JAPAN WOULD HAVE
BEEN A WRECK BY NOW.
OH? YOU WOULD THINK
A PATRIOT LIKE THAT
WOULD GIVE
A DAMN ABOUT
THE OLD CAPITAL.
HIS HANDS ARE TIED
LIKE OURS, IBUSE,
WHICH IS WHY WE
HAVE TO GO TO A LESS
THAN OPTIMAL PLAN B.
WHAT?
WE'LL HAVE TO CALL IN
THE CLEANUP CREW.
Gennai: WE'RE HERE.
Aoi: THOSE ARE SOME
STRANGE-LOOKING BUILDINGS.
[scoffs] MOST OF 'EM
GOT SO CONTAMINATED,
EVEN A PIG
WOULDN'T LIVE THERE.
THEY USED TO BE
MAJESTIC MONUMENTS
TO SCIENCE.
NOW THEY'RE JUST
WITHERING HEAPS OF RUST.
WE JUST PASSED GATE ONE,
WHICH CAN ONLY BE
OPENED OR CLOSED
FROM THE INSIDE.
IF AN INTRUDER
TRIES TO GET IN,
A SIREN SOUNDS, AND
THE GATE IS ELECTRIFIED.
[radio whines]
Mishima: NARUSE, COME IN.
VICE PRINCIPAL.
WHAT'S THE LATEST
ON THE HELICOPTER?
I CAN'T SAY THAT
I HAVE GOOD NEWS.
WE'VE BEEN ORDERED
TO GO TO THE CONFERENCE
AS SECURITY.
NO WAY!
HOW ARE WE
GOING TO HANDLE THIS
WITHOUT ANY SUPPORT?
CALM DOWN.
THE CONFERENCE WILL BE
OVER IN THREE DAYS.
THREE DAYS.
BUT THAT'S
PRETTY LONG.
Mishima: YOU'LL JUST
HAVE TO HANG IN THERE.
I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HOLD OUT FOR
ANOTHER THREE DAYS.
WE CAN DO IT, SIR.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
BY YOURSELF, THOUGH.
I'LL MOBILIZE SOMETHING
FROM THIS END.
HUH?
Aoi: HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
Kurobe: HOME, SWEET HOME.
IT'S THE LARGEST SAFE ZONE
IN THIS CITY.
WE CALL IT THE PLANET.
[computerized]
WELCOME TO THE PLANET,
HOME TO THE SCIENCE
OF THE FUTURE.
WOW. IT'S SO COOL.
IT'S LIKE
A SPACE STATION.
Kurobe: HMPH.
WHEN YOU'VE LIVED HERE
AS LONG AS WE HAVE,
IT CAN FEEL
LIKE A PRISON.
[computerized]
FIRST-TIME VISITORS,
PLEASE REGISTER
IN THE LOBBY
TO BECOME A MEMBER.
Aoi: CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S A HUMANOID ROBOT!
WHY DON'T YOU
INTRODUCE YOURSELF?
I AM YOUR ROBOT GUIDE
TO JASA.
MY NAME IS NO-SENSE.
MASTER GENNAI
GAVE ME THIS NAME
BECAUSE I
POSSESS A HEART
RICH IN EMOTIONS.
UH...
YOU MIGHT
WANT TO CONSIDER
A DIFFERENT NAME.
HE POSSESSES
ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE,
BUT HAS TO BE TOLD
EVERY LITTLE THING
TO UNDERSTAND.
COOL.
MY NAME'S AOI
THE BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT'S UP?
MISS AOI
THE BEAUTIFUL.
REGISTRATION
COMPLETE.
Kurobe: SO WHAT
DO WE NEED TO DO
TO TAKE CARE
OF THE GIRL
WITH THE GLASSES?
Ibara: SHE'S GOING
TO NEED A LOT OF OXYGEN
TO HELP HER HEAL.
Gennai: HMM.
HEY, THERE'S
THE OXYGEN CHAMBER.
I USE IT
FOR ANTI-AGING
TREATMENTS.
WE'RE GONNA NEED
TO CLEAN IT.
THAT DAMN THING REEKS
OF OLD-MAN ODORS.
[chuckles]
Taeko: IBARA.
I'M SORRY.
I'VE BECOME
A BURDEN TO YOU
WHEN YOU WERE
COUNTING ON ME THE MOST.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU SHOWED
COURAGE IN SAVING
A PREGNANT WOMAN.
IBARA'S RIGHT,
AND THIS GIVES ME
AN OPPORTUNITY
TO SHOW I CAN
KICK SOME BUTT
WHILE YOU'RE OUT,
SO TAKE YOUR TIME
RESTING UP.
UH, OK.
THAT'S VERY
REASSURING,
AOI.
[door slides open]
Gojiro:
ARE YOU OKAY,
IBUKI?
I'M FINE, DAD.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU KNOW, I JUST CAN'T
THANK YOU THREE ENOUGH.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE,
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY,
YOU SAVED THE BABY.
ACTUALLY, MY BODY
KIND OF ACTED
ON ITS OWN.
[stomach grumbles]
[groans]
I JUST REALIZED
HOW HUNGRY I AM.
OK. THEN LET'S ALL
GO GET SOME LUNCH.
IT'S MY TREAT.
ALL RIGHT, THEN!
LET'S EAT!
Ibara: YOU KNOW,
I GOTTA SAY,
YOU GUYS MUST NEED
A LOT OF ELECTRICITY
TO POWER THIS PLACE.
IT DOES TAKE
A LOT OF ELECTRICITY,
BUT IT CAN BE PROVIDED
WHEN YOU HAVE
A STEADY ENERGY SOURCE.
YOU MEAN SOMETHING
LIKE SOLAR POWER?
WELL, THAT WOULDN'T
BE ENOUGH.
INSTEAD, WE RELY
ON WATERPOWER.
WATERPOWER?
RIVER POWER
TO BE PRECISE.
WE BUILT
A HYDROELECTRIC SYSTEM
UPSTREAM.
Aoi: WOW.
WATERPOWER
IS AWESOME.
YOU CAN'T
CREATE STABLE ENERGY
USING WATERPOWER.
[stammers]
UM...
UH, WELL...
DON'T MIND ME.
WE HAVE ARRIVED.
THIS IS
THE MULTIPURPOSE HALL.
[both gasp]
[wind blowing]
[birds chirping]
Aoi: WOW.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
Ibara: THEY'VE
GOT GRASS
GROWING HERE,
AND THERE'S FISH
IN THE STREAM.
[gasps]
THIS WAS
A MASSIVE
PROJECT.
THEY RECREATED
THE ENTIRE
NATURAL WORLD
IN HERE.
ACTUALLY THEY
REALLY WANTED
THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE.
IT'S STRANGE.
I COULDN'T
HAVE IMAGINED
THAT THE WORLD
OUTSIDE
WOULD WITHER
AWAY FIRST.
IT'S QUITE
THE IRONY.
Mishima: WHAT?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU WELL,
MUSHANOKOJI.
CAN YOU GET ME
IN CONTACT WITH
THE CLEANUP CREW?
AS I WAS TRYING
TO TELL YOU,
VICE PRINCIPAL,
THIS IS
A CLEAR VIOLATION
OF THE LAW.
PRESENTLY, SIR,
YOUR JURISDICTION
IS SOLELY LIMITED
TO THE MEDICAL UNIT
OF COPPELION
HEADED
BY IBARA NARUSE.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO CONTACT ANY MEMBER
OUTSIDE YOUR GROUP.
ONLY THE PRIME MINISTER
COULD MAKE THAT KIND
OF AN EXCEPTION FOR YOU.
MUSHANOKOJI...
WOULD YOU BE
INTERESTED IN EATING
THE MOST
DELICIOUS SUKIYAKI
IN ALL OF KYOTO?
YES, I WOULD.
HUH?
THIS IS VICE
PRINCIPAL MISHIMA.
CHANNEL THREE,
CLEANUP CREW,
COME IN.
Boy: WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU, VICE PRINCIPAL?
I WANT YOU TO RENDEZVOUS
WITH THE MEDICAL UNIT
IMMEDIATELY.
THE MEDICAL UNIT?
OH, YOU MEAN
CLASS PRESIDENT
IBARA NARUSE.
ROGER THAT, VICE PRINCIPAL.
I'M ON MY WAY.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Ibara: THE FIRST DIVISION...
THE GHOST'S LAIR...
THE WHITE COAT...
A HEAVY RESPONSIBILITY...
A CURSE, PITIFUL CREATURES...
A CAREFULLY THOUGHT-OUT PLAN...
THE SIMPLE THINGS...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
PLANET.