[brakes squeal]
WHAT THE?
SOMEONE'S THERE.
[gasps]
IT CAN'T BE.
HEY,
CHECK IT OUT, SIS.
COMPANY.
["Angel" by angela playing]
...THE HELL?
WHO ARE THOSE GIRLS?
THEY GOT
SCHOOL UNIFORMS, TOO.
ARE THEY
YOUR CLASSMATES?
Taeko: AREN'T THEY
THE OZU SISTERS?
WE NEED TO TELL HARUTO.
Haruto: CHANNEL THREE,
COME IN.
THIS IS HARUTO KUROSAWA.
WHAT'S THE STATUS
OF YOUR CLEANUP MISSION?
OZU SISTERS, RESPOND.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE THEY THE REST
OF THE CLEANUP CREW
HE MENTIONED?
THEY'RE WITH HIM?
Kurobe: HMM.
I'M NOT SURE
WHAT THEY'RE UP TO,
BUT IT DOESN'T
SEEM GOOD.
Ibara: THEY MUST
HAVE BEEN THE ONES
WHO BLOCKED THE ROADS.
SHE LIFTED IT?!
Ibara: BACK UP!
Kurobe: DAMN IT.
[all groan]
HUH?
HMM?
[both chuckle]
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT?
YOU CALL THIS
A RESCUE MISSION?
WHY ARE YOUR PEOPLE
THE ONES THAT ARE
COMING AT US NOW?
I JUST DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE NOT TOLD MUCH
ABOUT THE OTHERS.
I NEED TO TALK
TO HARUTO.
DAMN! THEY'RE RIGHT
ON OUR TAIL NOW.
[passengers yelling]
DAMN IT!
I CAN'T STEER THE TRUCK!
WE'RE GONNA CRASH!
[crash]
HEY, A COFFEE SHOP.
WHAT'S THIS
FRIGGING TRUCK
FOR, ANYWAY?
I DON'T KNOW, SIS.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
DON'T MOVE!
WHAT'S
YOUR DEAL?
DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE DOING?
ANSWER ME,
OZU SISTERS!
WELL, LOOK WHO IT IS,
IBARA NARUSE.
ARE YOU STILL
TRYING TO ACT
LIKE THE CLASS PREZ
OR SOMETHING?
WELL, GUESS WHAT.
WE'RE NOT IN SCHOOL ANYMORE!
[giggles]
[chuckles]
THAT'S ENOUGH.
TRY THIS ON
FOR SIZE!
DANG IT.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
YEAH, I DID.
THE CELLS
OF A COPPELION
ARE MODIFIED
TO GIVE EACH OF US
A UNIQUE ABILITY.
AS I RECALL,
THE YOUNGER SISTER,
SHION OZU,
HAS EXTREMELY
ENHANCED SKELETAL
AND MUSCULAR SYSTEMS.
Kurobe: A CHICK
WITH SUPERHUMAN STRENGTH,
BUT WITHOUT THE BRAINS
TO GO WITH IT, HUH?
WHAT'S UP,
CLASS PRESIDENT
IBARA NARUSE?
WE HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN A WHILE.
HOW'S YOUR
SIGHTSEEING TOUR GOING?
YOU GIRLS HAVING FUN?
I KNOW WE'RE
HAVING A BLAST HERE.
WE FINALLY GOT
TO BREAK AWAY
FROM OUR
LAME-ASS TOUR GROUP.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
THAT WE'RE ALL PART
OF THE SELF-DEFENSE FORCE?
SELF-DEFENSE FORCE?
[laughing]
TELL YOU WHAT, THEN.
AS OF RIGHT NOW,
WE OFFICIALLY QUIT.
[grunts]
RUN, TAEKO!
[both gasp]
MY EYES! MY EYES!
A FLASH GRENADE.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
THAT BITCH
GETS ON MY NERVES.
[radio whines]
CHANNEL TWO,
THIS IS HARUTO KUROSAWA.
NARUSE, I'M STARTING
TO GET A BAD FEELING
OVER HERE.
BY ANY CHANCE,
ARE THE CLEANUP CREW'S
OZU SISTERS
GIVING YOU
ANY TROUBLE AT ALL?
Ibara: ARE YOU KIDDING?!
THEY ALMOST KILLED US!
Kurobe: ...TEACHING BACK
AT THAT SCHOOL OF YOURS?!
Haruto: ALL RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU'RE DEALING WITH.
THE OZU SISTERS
ARE TWINS,
CREATED USING THE SAME
CLONE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MADE US.
THEY WERE PRODUCED
BY INJECTING
LIVING NUCLEI
FROM A CERTAIN ACTRESS
INTO TWO ENUCLEATED,
UNFERTILIZED EGGS.
A CERTAIN ACTRESS, HMM?
THERE'S A MOTHER
OF THOSE MANIACS?
NO, THEY ARE
AN IDENTICAL COPY
OF THAT ACTRESS.
WE COPPELION
ARE ALL CLONES
OF EXISTING PEOPLE.
THEREFORE,
WE DON'T HAVE MOTHERS
IN THE STANDARD
BIOLOGICAL SENSE.
CONTAMINATION RESISTANCE
AND SPECIAL ABILITIES
WERE ADDED
TO EACH CLONE.
THEN THEY WERE STORED
IN AN INVENTORY
AS THOUGH THEY WERE
GENETICALLY MODIFIED
PRODUCE.
MUCH OF THE ORIGINAL
GENETIC CODE
IS PASSED ON AS IS,
INCLUDING
THEIR JUDGMENTS
AND BEHAVIORISMS,
SO THEIR TRAITS
ARE INSIDE OUR BRAINS.
THE FACT
OF THE MATTER
IS THE ACTRESS,
KUON OZU,
THE TWIN'S CLONE SOURCE,
WAS SECRETLY
A SERIAL KILLER.
[camera flash clicks]
OH, OF COURSE.
SO THEN
THE OZU SISTERS POSSESS
THE SAME PERSONALITY?
THEY'RE PSYCHOPATHS?
HOPEFULLY THEY'RE
NOT AS BAD AS KUON.
IF THEY
START GETTING
ANY FUNNY IDEAS...
Kanon: OK,
THIS IS IT.
THEY'RE
DEFINITELY
HIDING
HERE IN THIS
SUPERMARKET.
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
YOU'VE GOTTA
BE KIDDING ME.
HOW'D SHE KNOW
WE'RE HIDING
IN HERE?
CRAP.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
KEEP IT DOWN,
GENNAI.
WE'LL GET OUT THROUGH
THE EMERGENCY EXIT.
CAN WE MAKE IT?
Shion: OH,
MISS CLASS PRESIDENT,
COME OUT, COME OUT
WHEREVER YOU ARE.
YOU KNOW
YOU WANT TO COME OUT
AND PLAY WITH US.
HEY, CANNED PEACHES.
THEY LOOK YUMMY.
HMM.
[gunshot]
HAH!
DAMN IT.
HOW'D SHE DODGE
THAT SHOT?
[footsteps]
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?
WHY'D YOU TWO
BLOCK THE ROAD?
[giggles]
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU KNEW,
BUT I WAS NEVER
YOUR BIGGEST FAN,
IBARA NARUSE.
HUH?
THAT'S WHY WE DECIDED
TO JOIN THESE GUYS.
[laughs]
Kanon: THERE'S
NOWHERE LEFT
FOR YOU TO RUN.
WE'VE SURROUNDED
THE ENTIRE AREA
WITH HIGH-LEVEL WASTE.
YOUR FIELD TRIP
ENDS HERE, IBARA NARUSE.
[panting]
I'M SORRY.
I HAVE TO GO
BACK IN THERE
AND HELP IBARA.
WAIT. COME BACK HERE.
YOUR WOUNDS
HAVEN'T HAD ENOUGH TIME
TO HEAL YET.
WELL, SHIT.
TAKE IBUKI
AND GOJIRO
BACK TO THE PLANET,
GENNAI.
CONSIDER IT DONE.
Kurobe:
HEY, KID, YOU THERE?
YES. WHAT IS IT?
WE'VE GOT
A BIG PROBLEM.
THOSE NUTSO SISTERS
AND THE FIRST DIVISION
HAVE CAPTURED
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND HERE.
[groans]
OZU SISTERS,
DON'T YOU KNOW
THEY'RE JUST USING YOU?
LISTEN TO ME.
THE FIRST DIVISION
HAS PUT TOGETHER
A PLAN TO...
COLLECT ALL
THE OLD CAPITAL'S WASTE.
THEN THEY'LL PUT THAT WASTE
AROUND THE OUTSIDE
OF THE SARCOPHAGUS,
WHICH ITSELF
WILL BE STUFFED
WITH EVERY PIECE
OF DYNAMITE THEY HAVE,
AND BLOW THE PLACE UP.
AND THEN THE ENTIRE WORLD
SUCCUMBS TO CONTAMINATION,
AND EVERYONE DIES.
IF YOU KNOW ALL THAT,
THEN WHY ARE--
[clink]
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
ONCE MANKIND
IS OBLITERATED,
THE WORLD WILL BELONG
TO US COPPELION.
WE'RE THE MOST SUPERIOR
RACE EVER.
HOW'S THAT FOR
THE MOST CHEESIEST
LINE, SHION?
[both laughing]
GOOD ONE!
LET'S TAKE OVER
THE WORLD!
[laughing]
HONESTLY,
THE TWO OF US
ARE IN A BAD MOOD
TODAY,
SO I'LL END THIS
RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS BAD.
SHE'S GONNA
GET KILLED.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I THINK THAT NARUSE
MIGHT HAVE
ONE OF MY NEWEST GRENADES
WITH HER IN HER PACK.
Kurobe:
YOUR NEWEST WHAT?
Ibara:
3, 2, 1...
ZERO!
[squeals] MY EARS!
IT'S AN ULTRASONIC
GRENADE! DAMN IT!
I GUESS SHE HAD ONE
OF THOSE, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, AND IT
SURE DOES WORK.
EAT THIS.
THIS WAY, IBARA.
GUESS WE'RE
PLAYING TAG.
NOW I'M
REALLY PISSED.
Soldier:
NEVER MIND THEM.
HUH?
THOSE SURVIVORS
CAN'T GO ANYWHERE
SINCE YOU'VE SURROUNDED
THIS AREA WITH WASTE.
YOU SHOULD USE
THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO HEAD
FOR THE SARCOPHAGUS.
HUH?
HMM?
AND YOU SHOULD
SHUT UP, MORON.
WE ARE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE
UNTIL WE KILL
EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
[panting]
HEY, WHAT'S
TAKING YOU
SO LONG, GENNAI?
SHH. BE QUIET.
LOOK OVER THERE.
THIS DAY KEEPS
GETTING BETTER,
DOESN'T IT?
THEY'RE TRYING
TO TRAP US HERE
TO BUY
THEMSELVES
MORE TIME!
IBARA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE CRAZY!
WOULD YOU STOP
BEING SO RECKLESS?
Soldier: FIRE!
[groans]
Kurobe: YEAH!
Gennai:
SHE OVERTOOK
THE TANK!
WAY TO GO!
OK, EVERYBODY IN.
[motorcycle roaring]
EH?
HEY!
LET'S PLAY
A GAME OF TAG!
Kurobe:
STEP ON IT, GENNAI!
IT'S NO USE.
THEY'RE GAINING
ON US FAST!
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
WE'VE GOTTA TRY
SOMETHING QUICK.
HAVING THIS TANK
SHOULD HELP,
AT LEAST.
W-WHAT?
THIS ENDS...
RIGHT NOW!
EAT THIS!
YOU'RE GOING
TO END THIS NOW?
HOW DO YOU PLAN
ON DOING THAT?
DOES
THE CANNON WORK?
YOU MEAN THIS?
HEY, HURRY,
AND DO SOMETHING.
DAMN.
LOOK FOR
SOME CANNON SHELLS.
CANNON SHELLS?
YAH!
I DON'T SEE ANY
OVER HERE, IBARA.
HEY, I FOUND SOMETHING.
IS THIS ONE?
HEY, SIS,
COME TAKE OVER
THE DRIVING.
ALL RIGHT.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[growls]
ROCKET PUNCH!
Kurobe:
DON'T FIGHT HERE.
GOT IT.
HUH?
I FOUND SOME SHELLS
DOWN HERE.
OK, GENNAI,
WE'RE LOCKED
AND LOADED.
LET'S BLOW
THAT BIKE TO BITS.
Kurobe: DAMN.
THE OLDER SISTER'S
ON OUR ASS.
[chuckles]
MEGATON PUNCH!
[gasps]
WHAT THE HELL?
YOU PUNCHED THROUGH
A HYDROGEN TANK.
YOU NEED TO LEARN
HOW TO CONTROL
YOUR OWN STRENGTH.
HAH!
[yells]
Ibara:
FIRE TO OUR SIX!
Gennai: YOU GOT IT!
AH, HELL, YEAH.
THAT SHOULD
TAKE CARE
OF THOSE TWO.
I DON'T KNOW,
THOUGH.
DO YOU THINK
THAT WE OVERDID
IT A LITTLE?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THE FLAMES LAST
ONLY AN INSTANT,
BUT THE OZU SISTERS
ARE DEFINITELY
GOING TO BE KNOCKED OUT
FOR A WHILE.
[all gasp]
Kurobe: HOLY CRAP.
DID THAT CHICK JUST USE
HER YOUNGER SISTER
AS A SHIELD?
HEH.
NOW YOU'VE DONE IT.
YOU'VE REALLY
PISSED ME OFF.
SO WHAT'S
HER SPECIAL ABILITY?
UM, I REALLY
DON'T KNOW.
[crackling]
HEH!
[grunts]
[thunder crashes]
OH, MY GOD.
W-WHAT WAS THAT?
IS THAT
HER SPECIAL ABILITY,
SHOOTING
ELECTRICITY?
I'M TOLD THEY WOVE
ELECTRIC EEL
SEQUENCES
INTO MY DNA.
WHAT THE HELL WAS
OUR BELOVED SCHOOL
THINKING?
THEY SHOULD HAVE
THOUGHT TWICE
ABOUT MESSING WITH
MY BODY LIKE THIS.
IN ORDER TO GET
THE RESCUE TEAMS
TO THE SITE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE,
THEY HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO PUSH THE BOUNDARIES
AND TIMING
OF THEIR RESEARCH.
THERE GOAL WAS
TO SAVE LIVES.
HUMAN EXPERIMENT WAS
NEVER THEIR INTENT.
[thunder crashes]
[gasping]
YOU KNOW WHAT,
CLASS PRESIDENT
IBARA NARUSE?
EVERYTHING YOU SAID
JUST SOUNDS LIKE
A LOT OF SILLY
WISHFUL THINKING TO ME.
ADMIT IT.
YOU'RE WORRIED
OUT OF YOUR MIND,
AREN'T YOU?
WE'RE NO DIFFERENT THAN
THESE CHEAP, DISPOSABLE
HAND WARMERS.
WE'RE MANUFACTURED
AND USED UP
WITHOUT
A SECOND THOUGHT,
AND THEN WHEN WE'RE
OF NO USE ANYMORE...
Haruto:
SO HOW LONG
WILL WE LIVE?
HUH?
Mishima:
WE'RE NOT SURE.
NOW IT'S ALL STARTING
TO MAKE SOME SENSE,
THE REASON WHY
YOU AND YOUR SCIENTISTS
DECIDED TO GIVE US
THE NAME COPPELION.
IT'S SO THAT
WHEN WE DIE OFF,
NONE OF YOU
WILL HAVE TO FEEL
ANY REMORSE OR GUILT.
AT SOME POINT,
WE'LL JUST DROP DEAD
LIKE A LAB RAT
DURING A TEST.
Kanon: DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT THAT MEANS,
IBARA NARUSE?
WE COPPELION ARE ALL
CONDEMNED TO DIE
SUDDENLY AND
WITHOUT ANY WARNING.
IT'LL JUST HAPPEN
ONE DAY.
THE WARMTH
IN OUR BODIES
WILL LEAVE US.
IT COULD BE
NEXT YEAR,
NEXT WEEK,
OR IT COULD EVEN
HAPPEN TONIGHT,
AND THAT'S IT.
WE'RE DONE.
NO ONE KNOWS
HOW LONG WE'LL
BE ALIVE.
IT CAN'T BE.
HMM?
DID THEY
REALLY SAY THAT,
BOTH HARUTO AND
THE VICE PRINCIPAL?
DO YOU
UNDERSTAND IT NOW?
WE ARE AT WAR
WITH HUMANITY.
EITHER WE'LL BE
THE ONES TO DIE FIRST,
OR WE DESTROY THEM
BEFORE WE LET THAT
HAPPEN.
YOU SHOULD REALLY
CONSIDER JOINING US.
IT WOULD BE SO GREAT.
WITH OUR
COMBINED EFFORTS,
WE'D BE
AN UNSTOPPABLE FORCE.
WE CAN KILL
THE VICE PRINCIPAL
TOGETHER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I REFUSE!
WHAT?
IT'S THEIR FAULT.
HOW CAN YOU?
IT'S THE HUMANS
WHO ARE RESPONSIBLE
FOR OUR PITIFUL FATE.
[sighs]
IT'S INEVITABLE.
ALL LIVING THINGS
WILL DIE.
THERE'S NOTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
GOD, YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
IT'S NOT LIKE DEATH
WILL GREET US PEACEFULLY
WHILE WE'RE LYING
IN OUR BEDS, YOU KNOW.
GET REAL!
THAT MORNING OF OUR
SEND-OFF CEREMONY,
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT I HAD A FEELING
I'D NEVER RETURN
TO OSAKA AGAIN.
MAYBE IT WAS
MY DNA TELLING ME
THAT I DIDN'T
HAVE THAT MUCH TIME
LEFT TO LIVE.
HMM.
OH.
SO IF WHAT YOU SAY
IS TRUE, KANON,
THEN I'LL LIVE MY LIFE
TO THE FULLEST HERE.
THAT WILL BE
GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
THAT WOULD
NEVER WORK FOR ME.
LOOK AT THIS FILTHY,
CONTAMINATED CITY,
THIS GODFORSAKEN PLACE
THAT HUMANS FEAR.
I WANT THE WHOLE WORLD
TO END UP LIKE THIS.
UNTIL I
MAKE THAT HAPPEN,
THE ELECTRICITY IN ME
WILL NOT BE STOPPED!
GET OUT OF THERE,
IBARA!
YOU WON'T GET AWAY.
[thunder crashes]
DIE!
[gasps]
IF YOU DECIDE TO BREAK
THE RULES, KANON OZU,
THEN YOU
GET PUNISHED!
WAY TO GO!
YOU TOOK HER DOWN
IN ONE PUNCH.
JUST TO BE SAFE,
I'M GOING
TO SEDATE THEM WITH
MY TRANQUILIZER GUN.
LET'S HOPE
IT WORKS ON THEM.
[sighs]
[dart thwips]
WELL, I COULD
TELL YOU THIS MUCH.
I DON'T WANT
TO TAKE THESE GIRLS
BACK TO THE PLANET
WITH US.
DID YOU SAY
WE'RE GOING BACK
TO THE PLANET?
BUT WE CAME
ALL THIS WAY OUT
TO GET
TO THE HOSPITAL.
AND THESE GIRLS
CHANGED OUR PLAN,
SO WE HAVE
TO GO BACK.
IT WON'T BE
THAT EASY.
HUH?
WAIT A SEC.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
THEY SURROUNDED
THE ENTIRE AREA
WITH WASTE?
THE BASTARDS HAVE US
TRAPPED IN HERE?
THE WIND IS
STARTING TO PICK UP.
MISS AOI,
I HAVE BROUGHT YOU
YOUR 3:00 SWEETS.
SWEETS?
NICE TRY THERE.
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ME
THAT EASY, MR. NO-SENSE.
LEAVE
THE SWEETS THERE.
THEN GET LOST!
WAIT! YOU'RE
REALLY LEAVING?
PLEASE COME BACK.
MISS AOI, WHY DO
YOU KEEP YOURSELF
LOCKED INSIDE
OF THIS STOREROOM?
I, NO-SENSE,
AM A ROBOT.
BUT I POSSESS
DEEP EMOTIONAL
SENSITIVITY.
HOWEVER,
SINCE THE DAY
I WAS CREATED,
I HAVE NEVER BEEN
OUTSIDE THE PLANET.
I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS
TO FEEL
THE WARM RAYS
OF THE SUN
OR THE FEELING
OF THE BREEZE
CARESSING MY CHEEK.
BUT YOU'RE
JUST A ROBOT.
EVEN IF A BREEZE
DID BLOW ON YOUR CHEEK,
I DON'T THINK
YOU'D FEEL IT.
THAT IS CORRECT.
I AM A ROBOT.
I AM BUT
AN IMITATION,
A MODEL BASED
ON A HUMAN BEING.
THAT IS WHY I
ENVY YOU, MISS AOI.
YOU POSSESS
FREE WILL
AND CAN GO OUTSIDE
TO FEEL THE BREEZE
AS YOU PLEASE.
YOU'RE BETTER OFF
NOT KNOWING
WHAT IT'S LIKE
ON THE OUTSIDE.
I MEAN, THE BREEZE
IN THIS CITY'S
SO CONTAMINATED.
MISS AOI.
Gennai, over radio:
HEY, NO-SENSE!
IT'S ME, GENNAI!
OPEN THE GATE!
CAN YOU REALLY
TELL FROM HERE?
YES. I HAVE
COUNTERS SET UP
ALL OVER THE CITY.
IF THE OZU SISTERS
DID SPREAD
HIGH-LEVEL WASTE
AROUND THIS AREA,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE READINGS
ON THIS MAP OF THOSE
SPECIFIC SPOTS.
OH, MY GOD!
LOOK AT THIS!
EVERYTHING THAT'S
SHOWING UP HERE
IS RISING ABOVE
CRITICAL LEVELS!
Ibara: THE ASTRONOMICAL
OBSERVATORY?
THE SUN DISAPPEARED.
HALT!
PUT YOUR HANDS UP!
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
TAKING
AN AFTERNOON STROLL.
I JUST GOT
TIRED OF WORKING
AT MY DESK.
THIS ONE IS
ALSO A COPPELION.
TAKE HIM IN.
[chirping]
HUH?
HEY, THE BIRD'S
FREAKING OUT.
SHUT UP! CAN'T YOU
SEE I'M BUSY?
[radio whines]
WE'RE AT THE NORTH SIDE
OF THE OBSERVATORY.
WE CAUGHT
ONE OF THE DOLLS.
WE'LL RENDEZVOUS
WITH YOU SHORTLY.
YOU SHOULD ESCAPE
WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
WHAT?
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
THE WASTE SHOULD BE SOUTH
OF THE ASTRONOMICAL
OBSERVATORY.
IT'S THE WIND.
THE WIND IS
CARRYING IT HERE.
PULL OUT!
NARUSE, THE WIND
IS ON ITS WAY.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Shion: EARTH'S WRATH...
NO ESCAPE...
THE TRAIN...
THE WIND DIRECTION...
ELECTRICAL SUBSTATION...
INTERNAL IONS...
OPERATION ELECTRIC RAILROAD...
THE FAKE SKY...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
DIVERSION.