NOW FIRE
AT THE TWO OF US!
WHERE'S NARUSE?
[crying]
Hmm?
Haruto: NARUSE!
["Angel" by angela playing]
NARUSE,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
COME ON, NARUSE.
SAY SOMETHING, ANYTHING.
SHE'S UNCONSCIOUS.
WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
Haruto:
TURN HER FACE-UP.
Kurobe: SHE'S
BADLY BLEEDING.
SHE'S LOSING
A LOT OF BLOOD.
[all gasp]
Kurobe: THERE'S
A PIECE OF SHRAPNEL
LODGED IN HER GUT.
SHE'S NOT BREATHING.
SHE'S IN CARDIAC ARREST.
EH? THAT'S NOT GOOD.
AOI FUKASAKU,
GO GRAB
THE A.E.D. KIT
FROM THE BACK
OF THE ARMORED
CARRIER.
HUH?
Haruto:
HEY, FUKASAKU.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NO. IBARA IS
GONNA DIE,
AND IT'S MY FAULT.
I'VE SCREWED
EVERYTHING UP AGAIN.
AOI FUKASAKU...
SHE'LL ONLY DIE
IF WE DON'T HELP.
EVERYONE HAS
TO DO THEIR PART
AND WORK TOGETHER
AS A TEAM
TO SAVE HER.
NOW GO GET ME
THE A.E.D.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
[gasps]
YES, KUROSAWA.
[grumbles]
HEY, KID,
THE BLEEDING
WON'T STOP.
I'M GONNA PULL OUT
THIS SHRAPNEL.
NO, DON'T.
KEEP APPLYING PRESSURE
AROUND THE WOUND
SO SHE
DOESN'T BLEED OUT.
[exhales]
HMM?
HEY, THE GUY
IN THE WHITE COAT
IS WOUNDED, TOO.
Haruto:
FORGET THAT BASTARD.
WE...HAVE...
TO...BE...QUICK.
KUROSAWA, IS THIS THING
THE A.E.D.?
THAT'S THE ONE!
NOW WHAT?
WE'LL GIVE HER HEART
AN ELECTRICAL JOLT.
HE CAN'T TAKE
THE SHOCK, THOUGH.
YOU'LL HAVE
TO PRESS DOWN
ON THE WOUND.
WHAT? I DON'T WANT
TO GET SHOCKED.
[whimpers]
FORGET IT, THEN.
IF YOU
REFUSE TO HELP,
STAY AWAY!
[A.E.D. unit whines]
CHARGED. GET BACK.
AH, SCREW IT. HOW BAD'S
A TINY, LITTLE JOLT ANYWAY?
MOVE IT, MISTER!
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?
SORRY,
BUT THIS IS MY JOB.
I'M GONNA DO MY PART
TO SAVE IBARA!
[chuckles]
THAT'S WELL SAID.
HERE IT GOES.
D-DID IT WORK?
SHH.
DAMN IT.
COME...ON...NARUSE.
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF RISKING YOUR LIFE
TO HELP A SCUMBAG
LIKE HIM?
HUMANS...AREN'T...WORTH...IT.
[grunting]
[beeps]
[gasps]
HEY.
SHE'S BREATHING.
LOOKS LIKE
YOU GUYS DID IT.
SHE'S LOSING
TOO MUCH BLOOD.
WE CAN'T
TREAT HER HERE.
THEN WE'LL TAKE HER
BACK TO THE PLANET.
WHAT ABOUT THAT GUY?
WHAT DO WE DO
WITH HIM?
HE'S STILL ALIVE,
YOU KNOW.
GO ON AHEAD.
I'LL STAY BEHIND
AND TIE HIM UP
SO HE
DOESN'T TRY
AND GET AWAY.
Haruto: OK.
WE'LL GO BACK.
[liquid bubbling]
HOW ARE YOU FEELING,
MISS TAEKO?
BETTER, THANK YOU.
Aoi:
HANG IN THERE, IBARA!
PLEASE,
JUST DON'T DIE!
[gasps]
WHAT HAPPENED
TO HER?
TAEKO, YOU GOTTA
DO SOMETHING.
SHE NEEDS
AN EMERGENCY OPERATION.
HOW ARE
YOUR SURGERY SKILLS?
THEY TAUGHT US
THE VERY BASICS
IN CLASS.
THERE'S
NOT MUCH TIME.
WE HAVE
TO START NOW.
OK. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I KNEW THAT WE COULD
COUNT ON YOU, TAEKO.
WITH THIS MUCH
BLEEDING,
I THINK SHE
NEEDS TO BE GIVEN
A TRANSFUSION.
CAN YOU DO IT?
Taeko: SHE'S
A THIRD-YEAR STUDENT.
YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT MEANS, RIGHT?
LET'S BEGIN
THE OPERATION.
MISS AOI, ARE YOU
NOT FEELING WELL?
YOU APPEAR DEPRESSED AND
EMOTIONALLY UNSTABLE.
THINGS WOULD
BE BETTER IF I
WEREN'T AROUND.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
A HELP TO ANYBODY.
I'M USUALLY
JUST IN THE WAY
OF THINGS.
WHY AM I SPILLING
MY GUTS TO A ROBOT,
ANYWAY?
Ibara: TAEKO.
[gasps]
WHERE AM I?
YOU'RE
AT THE PLANET,
IBARA.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
YOU DON'T SEEM
TO HAVE ANY
COMPLICATIONS.
COMPLICATIONS?
WE GAVE YOU
A SIGNIFICANT
BLOOD TRANSFUSION.
OH, REALLY? NO WONDER.
THAT'S WHY MY INSIDES
FEEL ALL WARM AND FUZZY.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
I CAN TELL YOUR BLOOD'S
HEALING ME UP ALREADY.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
HOW IT WORKS, IBARA?
AS COPPELION,
OUR BLOOD TYPES
ARE MATCHED
BY OUR INDIVIDUAL
GRADE LEVELS.
THEREFORE, A THIRD-YEAR
REQUIRES
A THIRD-YEAR'S BLOOD.
[sighs]
IT'S HARUTO'S?
WOW.
IT'S BEEN
ONE HELL OF A DAY.
Announcer: WE'RE BRINGING YOU
THIS LIVE COVERAGE TODAY
FROM THE NATIONAL DIET BUILDING,
WHERE
AN INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE
IS ABOUT TO TAKE PLACE.
THE CONFERENCE WILL BE HELD
OVER THE NEXT THREE DAYS.
THERE'S A HEAVY FOCUS
ON JAPAN
AND WHETHER OR NOT
IT'S EQUIPPED TO LEAD
THE WORLD'S TRANSITION
TO NEXT-GENERATION ENERGY.
YOU GET TV HERE?
YEAH. WE HAVE
A SATELLITE DISH
INSTALLED HERE.
WHOA. THE BABY JUST
GAVE A LITTLE KICK.
REALLY?
DO YOU WANT TO TRY
TO FEEL IT?
UH...
CAN YOU HEAR
ITS HEART BEATING?
I CAN.
WE NEED THE RESCUE TEAM
TO GET HERE SOON.
DIDN'T THEY
GIVE YOU TRAINING
FOR DELIVERING
BABIES?
I THOUGHT YOU GIRLS
COULD DO ANYTHING.
NO ONE THOUGHT WE'D
FIND A PREGNANT WOMAN
IN THE OLD CAPITAL.
Ibara: HEY!
HUH?
TAEKO!
IBARA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
HAVE YOU SEEN
AOI AROUND?
I CAN'T SEEM
TO FIND HER
ANYWHERE.
WELL, ABOUT THAT...
[pounding]
Ibara: HEY!
OPEN UP, AOI!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ALL COOPED UP IN THERE?
IT'S TIME
FOR BREAKFAST.
OPEN THIS DOOR
RIGHT NOW!
[groans]
YOU DON'T HAVE
A KEY TO THIS ROOM,
MISS IBUKI?
NOT EVEN A SPARE?
I'M SORRY.
SHE LOCKED HERSELF IN
WITH THE ONLY ONE
WE HAVE.
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON WITH
THAT GIRL, ANYWAY?
TAEKO AND I ARE
OUT OF COMMISSION
WITH OUR INJURIES.
SHE NEEDS
TO TAKE UP
THE SLACK.
SHE'S PROBABLY
FEELING GUILTY,
THINKING SHE'S TO BLAME
FOR YOUR INJURIES.
YOU THINK SO?
HER CAPTURE IS WHAT
PUT US IN THIS MESS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
MAYBE YOU COULD
GIVE HER A LITTLE
PEP TALK, IBARA.
I BET THAT WOULD
MAKE HER FEEL BETTER.
GIVE IT A TRY.
AOI, I KNOW
THAT YOU'RE FEELING
REALLY BADLY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
LOCKING YOURSELF
IN THIS ROOM
AND HIDING FROM
YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES
JUST MAKES YOU...
A LOSER.
[sobs]
OR EVEN WORSE,
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING.
[sobbing]
IS THAT HOW YOU
WANT TO BE SEEN, AOI?
[crying]
HELLO?
ARE YOU LISTENING, AOI?
[yawns]
HEY, KUROBE.
I BROUGHT
THE COPPELION BOY
WITH ME.
I DON'T KNOW THIS PLACE.
WHERE ARE WE?
A POLICE STATION,
OF COURSE.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO
BRING THAT BASTARD
BACK WITH US
TO THE PLANET.
Kurobe:
DAMN WHITE-COAT FREAK.
HE DOESN'T WEAR
AN OXYGEN TANK.
HE MUST HAVE
A SERIOUS DEATH WISH.
[chuckles]
Kurobe: WHATEVER.
HE JUST GIVES ME
THE CREEPS.
WHO ARE YOU GUYS
WORKING FOR?
WHY ARE YOU COLLECTING
ALL THAT WASTE?
Haruto: AND NOT
JUST THE LOW-LEVEL WASTE
AT THE WATER TREATMENT
PLANT,
BUT THE HIGH-LEVEL WASTE
IN THE BOAT RACE
STADIUM AS WELL.
CURIOUSLY
ALL THE CANISTERS
WERE LABELED IN ENGLISH,
INDICATING THEY CAME
FROM OVERSEAS.
ARE YOU WORKING WITH
THE BACK-END COMPANY
YELLOW CAKE?
I DON'T KNOW
OF ANY YELLOW CAKE.
WE'RE NOT DOING THIS
FOR MONEY.
OH, SO NOW YOU TALK?
Haruto: THEN WHAT
ARE YOU AFTER?
SO YOU DON'T WANT
TO TELL ME THAT, DO YOU?
[gunshot]
WHAT THE HELL?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO SHOOT HIM.
HUH?
[laughing]
IT'S A NEUROTOXIN.
WITHOUT THIS ANTIDOTE,
YOU'LL HAVE FIVE SECONDS
UNTIL YOU'RE DEAD.
THAT'S HOW LONG
YOU HAVE TO ANSWER ME.
5...
WAIT A SECOND, KID.
4...
HE HAS NO FEAR OF PAIN...
3...
OR DYING.
2...
[gasping]
AND 1.
WAIT. I'LL TELL YOU.
[gunshot]
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
DID HE JUST
BEG FOR HIS LIFE?
IF HE WAS
READY TO DIE,
THEN HE WOULD
HAVE COMMITTED
SUICIDE ALREADY.
THAT WOULD PROTECT
THE FIRST DIVISION'S SECRET.
BUT HE HAS A REASON
FOR WANTING TO STAY ALIVE.
THERE'S
NO STOPPING US NOW.
WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT ARE
YOU SAYING?
THE FIRST DIVISION
HAS NO LEADER.
EVERY LAST SOLDIER
IS PROBABLY ON HIS WAY
TO THE SARCOPHAGUS
TO CARRY OUT
HIS MISSION.
THE SARCOPHAGUS?
WE'RE COLLECTING
ALL OF THE WASTE
AT THE SARCOPHAGUS.
FROM THERE,
WE WILL SPREAD TERROR
THROUGHOUT
THE ENTIRE WORLD.
[laughs]
HUH?
Haruto:
NARUSE, COME IN.
HARUTO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
[whimpers]
[gasps]
Taeko:
MISS IBUKI.
THE BABY'S COMING.
THE BABY'S
COMING NOW?
[gasping]
OH, NO.
Gojiro: IBUKI!
ARE YOU HAVING
CONTRACTIONS AGAIN?
I CAN'T
STAND UP.
HER CONTRACTIONS ARE
GETTING CLOSER TOGETHER.
CALL THE RESCUE HELICOPTER
IMMEDIATELY!
[German accent]
WE ALL KNOW AUSTRALIA
IS POWERFUL
AND HAS THE LARGEST
NATURAL RESOURCE.
PLEASE CONSIDER
AN EXCLUSIVE AGREEMENT
WITH ITALY.
NO, NO!
PLEASE CONSIDER FRANCE!
WHAT?
YOU'RE SAYING
THE WOMAN IS ABOUT
TO GO INTO LABOR?
YES, SIR.
IT LOOKS THAT WAY.
WE NEED MORE
MEDICAL ASSISTANCE.
CAN YOU SEND
A HELICOPTER OVER NOW?
IF ONLY IT WAS
MY CALL, NARUSE,
BUT THE PRIME MINISTER
HAS MADE THIS CONFERENCE
THE HIGHEST PRIORITY.
HE'S TRYING TO DISPLAY
JAPAN'S POWER
SO THAT HE CAN PRESERVE
THE COUNTRY'S DIGNITY.
AND THAT'S A GOOD REASON
HE WON'T SEND EVEN
A SINGLE HELICOPTER OUT?
MR. GOJIRO,
IS SHE HOLDING UP OK?
JUST FOR NOW,
BUT SHE'S
GONNA GIVE BIRTH
WITHIN TWO DAYS.
THE HELICOPTER,
WHERE IS IT?
YOU HEAR THAT?
[rotors whirring]
[sighs]
Kurobe:
I'M TELLING YOU,
THIS BASTARD'S
COMPLETELY NUTS.
[chuckles]
EVEN IF IT IS
THEIR GOAL,
IS THE FIRST
DIVISION CAPABLE
OF SUCH A THING?
IMAGINE...
THE SARCOPHAGUS
CONSTRUCTED AROUND
THE ACCIDENT SITE
IS FILLED WITH DEADLY
CONTAMINATED MATERIALS.
IN A WAY,
IT'S LIKE A MASSIVE BOMB.
JUST HAVING IT THERE
IS DANGEROUS ENOUGH.
BUT WHAT IF SOMEONE
DETONATES IT?
IT WOULD BE
COMPLETELY DESTROYED,
AND THE COUNTRY
WITH IT AS WELL.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
THE FIRST DIVISION
HOLDS A SERIOUS GRUDGE
AGAINST
THE JAPANESE GOVERNMENT.
THEY SHOULD
COMPLAIN DIRECTLY
TO THE PRIME MINISTER
THEN!
COME ON.
CALM DOWN, KUROBE.
I'M SURE HE'LL
FIND OUT ABOUT IT SOON.
NARUSE
HAS ALREADY REPORTED
TO THE VICE PRINCIPAL
AND GIVEN HIM
ALL THE DETAILS.
[cheering]
[growls]
VICE PRINCIPAL
MISHIMA, OVER HERE.
OUGAI.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU'VE ASCERTAINED
WHAT THE FIRST DIVISION
IS PLANNING.
I HAVE, AND
THE PRIME MINISTER
SHOULD BE UPDATED.
WE NEED REINFORCEMENTS
SENT A.S.A.P.
I WON'T TELL HIM
ANYTHING
THAT COULD NEGATIVELY
IMPACT HIS LEADERSHIP
AT THIS CONFERENCE.
WHAT'S THAT?
THIS WHOLE THING
MAY SEEM SILLY TO YOU,
BUT IF WE FALL BEHIND
THE REST OF THE WORLD,
OUR NATION
WILL BE AT RISK.
JUST WAIT UNTIL
THE CONFERENCE IS OVER.
UNTIL THEN, I'LL LEAVE
THE FATE OF JAPAN
TO THOSE CUTE
LITTLE DOLLS OF YOURS.
[sighs]
THE FOREMAN
HAS RETURNED HOME.
Gojiro: WHAT?!
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
THEY CAN'T?
WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE?
TAKE YOUR FIGHT
OUTSIDE!
FOREMAN,
LISTEN TO THIS.
THE SO-CALLED HELPERS
ARE GOING TO ABANDON
MY DAUGHTER!
A HELICOPTER
WON'T BE HERE
FOR TWO DAYS!
APPARENTLY
SOME STUPID CONFERENCE
IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN
THE LIFE OF A CITIZEN.
SO HAS IBUKI
ENTERED INTO LABOR YET?
YEAH,
AND TO BE CLEAR,
I DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT DELIVERING
BABIES.
Gojiro: IF WE DON'T
GET HER TO THE HOSPITAL,
WE COULD END UP
LOSING BOTH OF THEM.
HOSPITAL? WEREN'T YOU
MAKING YOUR WAY
TO THE CITY'S HOSPITAL
WHEN THE FIRST DIVISION
ATTACKED YOU?
HMM. THEY WERE,
AND THAT'S WHERE WE HAVE
OUR HEADQUARTERS SET UP.
WHAT ARE
YOU THINKING?
DO YOU
WANT TO GET ATTACKED
BY THE GHOSTS AGAIN?
I DIDN'T SAY
WE'RE GOING ANYWHERE.
BUT THIS TIME,
I WON'T LET THEM ATTACK.
HUH?
EH?
[radio whines]
HARUTO, COME IN.
I'M HERE, NARUSE.
WE'RE GONNA
MAKE OUR WAY
TO THE OLD
DOWNTOWN AREA.
KEEP AN EYE
ON THINGS FOR US.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU NEARLY DIED
YESTERDAY, REMEMBER?
THANKS TO THE BLOOD
YOU DONATED, THOUGH,
I'M OK.
OH, LOOK AFTER
AOI FOR ME,
BECAUSE SHE KIND OF
LOCKED HERSELF UP
IN A STORAGE ROOM.
[sighs]
TO DOWNTOWN!
WE'LL GET YOU
TO THAT HOSPITAL,
MISS IBUKI.
[engine idling]
HURRY UP.
WE HAVEN'T GOT
ALL DAY, YOU KNOW.
KUROBE, WHERE
SHOULD I PLACE
THE WEAPONS?
BY THE DOORS. MAKE SURE
THEY DON'T GO INSIDE
THE SHELTER TRAILER.
TAKE IT SLOWLY NOW.
OK. THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS IS NO-SENSE.
WHERE IS
EVERYONE GOING?
DOWNTOWN
TO THE HOSPITAL.
TAKE GOOD CARE
OF AOI, NO-SENSE.
UNDERSTOOD,
MISS IBARA.
I WILL NURSE
AND FEED MISS AOI
DURING
HER CONVALESCENCE.
Kurobe: OK,
EVERYBODY ON BOARD?
Ibara:
LET'S GET MOVING.
[truck horn honks]
AH, LOOK AT THIS.
IT REALLY IS
A BIG SHELTER SPACE.
SO WHAT'S
THE BEST WAY TO GO
TO GET
TO THE HOSPITAL?
Kurobe: DON'T WORRY.
I KNOW ALL THE ROADS
AND OVERPASSES
THIS THING
CAN MAKE IT THROUGH.
WE'LL START
BY HEADING NORTH
TO GET ONTO
THE HIGHWAY.
THAT'LL PUT US RIGHT
IN THE DOWNTOWN AREA
OF THE OLD CAPITAL,
WHERE THE HOSPITAL'S
LOCATED.
[static buzzing]
CLEANUP CREW,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
RESPOND IF YOU
CAN HEAR THIS.
Ibara: HARUTO, IT'S ME.
IT'S LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
GONNA GET TO THE HOSPITAL
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
WERE YOU TALKING
TO SOMEBODY JUST NOW?
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO GET IN CONTACT
WITH THE OTHER MEMBERS
OF THE CLEANUP CREW.
IT'S A PAIN WHEN THEY
DISAPPEAR ALL THE TIME
LIKE THIS.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
YOU NEED TO GET ALONG
WITH YOUR GROUP.
OH, YEAH. THANKS FOR
THE FREE ADVICE.
WELL,
KEEP YOUR GUARD UP
WHILE YOU'RE
OUT THERE, NARUSE.
THE FIRST DIVISION
WILL SURELY COME
AFTER YOU.
Ibara: WHAT? I THOUGHT
THE FIRST DIVISION
WAS HEADED
FOR THE SARCOPHAGUS.
THEY STILL NEED
SOMETHING, THOUGH.
DO YOU KNOW
WHY THOSE GUYS
ARE CHASING AFTER
US COPPELION?
HOLD ON.
THEY NEED
TO USE US
TO GET IN.
EXACTLY, TAEKO NOMURA.
THE FIRST DIVISION
NEEDS TO HAVE A COPPELION
IN ORDER TO BE
ABLE TO GAIN ACCESS
INTO THE SARCOPHAGUS.
THAT'S BECAUSE
THE SARCOPHAGUS ITSELF
HAS BECOME
A MASSIVE ZONE.
ANY HUMAN EXPOSED TO IT
WOULD BE KILLED INSTANTLY,
EVEN WITH A HAZMAT SUIT.
BUT NOT US,
'CAUSE WE ARE
IMMUNE TO THAT TYPE
OF ENVIRONMENT.
OH, I SEE.
THEY CAN'T GET
INSIDE THE SARCOPHAGUS
WITHOUT ONE OF US
WITH THEM.
CORRECT. THOSE GUYS
NEED YOU ALIVE, NARUSE.
IF THEY CAPTURE YOU,
THEY SHOULDN'T
GO TOO ROUGH ON YOU.
BUT STILL...
[groans]
HEY, WATCH IT.
[gasps]
[counter beeping]
Kurobe: THE COUNTER'S
GOING CRAZY.
ITS READING
IS REALLY HIGH.
COULD THE ZONE
REACH THIS FAR OUT?
[all gasp]
THIS ISN'T RIGHT,
KUROBE.
IT'S NOT LISTED
ON THE MAP.
MAYBE A NEW ZONE
HAS APPEARED.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'M GOING
TO BACK IT UP ANYWAY.
WAIT. OVER THERE.
THAT DRUM.
[gasps]
THE COVER IS OPEN.
YOU DON'T THINK...
HIGH-LEVEL WASTE.
Kurobe: WHO SAID
THEY WON'T BE TOO ROUGH?
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL JUST TAKE
A DIFFERENT ROUTE.
IT'S STRANGE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HOW IS IT STRANGE?
THAT STUFF'S
VERY HAZARDOUS.
WHO COULD HAVE
BROUGHT IT HERE?
[static crackles]
NONE OF THEM
ARE RESPONDING
ON THE RADIO.
WHO? YOUR FRIENDS?
"FRIENDS,"
SUCH A MEANINGLESS WORD.
[laughs]
Kurobe: OK,
HEADING THIS FAR SOUTH
SHOULD LET US
AVOID THE ZONE.
JUST GO OVER HERE NOW,
AND WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
[counter beeping]
HUH?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING!
Gennai:
ANOTHER ONE.
I BET
ALL THE STREETS
ARE BLOCKED
WITH THOSE.
IS THERE ANY
OTHER ROAD NEARBY
YOU CAN TAKE
THIS THING ON?
THAT'S WHAT I'M
WORKING ON NOW. HMM?
THE FREEWAY.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'LL TAKE US
RIGHT
TO THE DOWNTOWN AREA
OF THE OLD CAPITAL.
I JUST NEED TO BACK UP
A BIT TO GET US ON THERE.
THIS IS KUROSAWA.
CLEANUP CREW,
WHERE ARE YOU?
PLEASE RESPOND,
OZU SISTERS.
Kurobe: ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE AT THE ON-RAMP
FOR THE FREEWAY.
THERE AREN'T
ANY ZONE READINGS
SO FAR.
HAH! THAT'LL SHOW
THOSE GHOSTS.
HERE WE COME.
HUH? [gasps]
[brakes squeal]
WHAT THE?
SOMEONE'S THERE!
[gasps]
IT CAN'T BE.
IS THERE A PROBLEM
ON THE ROAD?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
IBARA?
DO YOU SEE SOMETHING?
HEY,
CHECK IT OUT, SIS.
COMPANY.
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Taeko: KANON AND SHION...
CROP BREEDING...
SPECIAL ABILITIES...
A SERIAL KILLER...
THE SARCOPHAGUS...
HUMAN EXPERIMENT...
GUILT...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
SISTERS.