[electricity crackling]
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M A DOLL, AND THAT'S
ALL I'LL EVER BE.
I WAS NEVER HUMAN
TO BEGIN WITH.
I'M NOTHING
BUT AN ANIMATED DOLL.
IS THAT IT,
MR. GENNAI?
YES, IT IS.
IN A LITTLE WHILE NOW,
THE SKYSCRAPERS
WILL BE PAINTED RED
WITH THE LIGHT
OF THE SETTING SUN.
I HOPE I GET TO SEE IT
WITH ALL OF YOU.
YOU WILL. I PROMISE.
HUH?
HMM.
[gasps]
HUH?
NO WAY.
["Angel" by Angela playing]
[both grunt]
HUH? WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT?
A GIANT
MECHANICAL SPIDER
IS TAILING US.
THAT'S THE IRON SPIDER.
IMPOSSIBLE.
I THOUGHT WE DESTROYED IT.
[gasps]
IS THAT KANON?
HOW IS IT
STILL MOVING?
EVEN IF ITS SYSTEMS
ARE FUNCTIONAL,
IT HAS
NO POWER SOURCE.
WELL, THAT EXPLAINS IT.
KANON'S USING HER ABILITY
TO GENERATE ELECTRICITY
TO POWER
THE SPIDER DIRECTLY.
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
Kurobe: GOJIRO, GIVE HER
EVERYTHING SHE'S GOT!
GO GRAB US
SOME WEAPONS.
RIGHT.
[groans]
WHAT'S WITH ALL
THAT NOISE OUT THERE?
SOMEBODY TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOU'VE GOTTA
BE KIDDING ME!
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?!
UH, I'M AFRAID SO,
LIEUTENANT IBUSE.
WELL, SHIT,
THAT'S JUST GREAT.
WE'RE ALREADY SHORT
ON TIME AS IS,
AND NOW THIS.
[radio whines]
Aoi: MAYDAY! MAYDAY!
HUH?
AOI FUKASAKU?
COME IN,
VICE PRINCIPAL!
THINGS ARE GOING CRAZY
OVER HERE!
THIS IS
IBUSE SPEAKING.
THE VICE PRINCIPAL
IS UNAVAILABLE
RIGHT NOW.
LISTEN TO ME, IBUSE.
WE NEED YOU TO COME
AND SAVE US RIGHT AWAY!
YOU NEED US
RIGHT NOW?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT SORT
OF PROBLEMS ARE
YOU GUYS HAVING?
WE'VE GOT
OUR OWN PROBLEMS
TO DEAL WITH
HERE,
SO THIS ISN'T
A GOOD TIME TO--
[screams]
[both gasp]
JUST HURRY UP,
AND COME GET US, OK?
I DON'T THINK WE CAN
HOLD OUT MUCH LONGER!
WE NEED YOUR HELP!
BUT EVEN IF WE
LEFT RIGHT NOW,
THE SOONEST
WE CAN GET TO YOU
IS IN 12 HOURS.
IT WOULDN'T BE UNTIL
AROUND SUNRISE WHEN
WE COULD ARRIVE.
THAT WILL BE FINE.
JUST GET HERE QUICKLY.
PLEASE DON'T ABANDON US
HERE TO DIE.
OK, OK. SETTLE DOWN,
AND DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE MOVING OUT
RIGHT NOW.
[cheering]
YOU BETTER HURRY UP,
VICE PRINCIPAL,
OR WE'LL LEAVE
WITHOUT YOU.
[groans]
IT CAUGHT UP TO US.
WHA?
WHERE DID IBARA GO?
HMPH.
GOOD.
YOU'RE HERE.
COME ON,
IBARA NARUSE.
LET'S SETTLE THIS
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
STOP THIS NONSENSE, KANON.
WHAT GOOD IS THIS
GOING TO DO?
WHY DO THIS?
WHY DO WE HAVE
TO END UP HURTING
ONE ANOTHER?
BECAUSE YOU SIDE
WITH THE ENEMY,
THE HUMANS!
BUT NOT ME.
I WON'T EVER FORGIVE
WHAT THEY'VE DONE.
HMM.
THEY DUMPED US
INTO THIS HELLHOLE,
INTO THIS
CONTAMINATED CITY.
I CAN SEE
THINGS CLEARLY
FROM UP HERE.
[laughs] IT'S JUST
AN ENDLESS LABYRINTH
OF CONCRETE.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING HERE AT ALL,
NOTHING!
THIS EMPTY,
DECAYING WORLD,
THIS IS WHERE
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO LIVE OUT
THE REST
OF OUR LIVES?!
NO, THANKS!
[gasps]
[yells]
HYAH!
[groans]
AH, DAMN IT.
SHE'S TRYING
TO DERAIL THE TRAIN.
[coughs]
KANON!
SHIT.
I'M BLEEDING.
I HATE THIS.
STUPID BLOOD.
YOU'VE GOT
TO STOP, SIS,
OR YOU'RE
GONNA DIE.
YOU NEED TO STAY PUT
AND REST, SHION.
I'LL PUT AN END
TO THIS SOON.
DON'T WORRY.
ONCE IT'S ALL OVER,
I'LL DIE WITH YOU,
BY YOUR SIDE.
AFTER THAT, YOU
WON'T HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THEM ANYMORE.
THOSE NIGHTMARES
THAT TORMENT YOU,
THEY'LL ALL GO AWAY.
HEY, CLASS PRESIDENT,
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO STOP THAT THING?
ARE YOU
LISTENING TO ME?
Aoi: IBARA!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?!
KANON IS
PREPARED TO DIE.
IF I DON'T
HELP HER QUICKLY,
IT'LL BE TOO LATE.
HUH?
YOU WANT TO HELP HER?
[chuckles]
Ibara: THOSE STEEL WIRES
WRAPPED AROUND
KANON'S FINGERS
ARE DRAINING EVERY LAST BIT
OF LIFE OUT OF HER.
SHE WON'T STOP,
SO I'LL HAVE
TO CUT THEM MYSELF.
Officer: YOU FOOL!
SHUT DOWN THAT CHOPPER!
Ibuse:
TRY AND STOP US!
GET THIS THING
IN THE AIR.
Mishima: IBUSE!
EH?
LET ME
ON THAT HELICOPTER!
VICE PRINCIPAL.
GUESS WE CAN
ALL SAY GOODBYE
TO OUR CAREERS NOW.
THE THIRD DIVISION
IS COMMITTING TREASON!
[grunts]
FIRE UP THE BOOSTERS!
WE'RE OSCAR MIKE.
SET A COURSE
FOR THE OLD CAPITAL.
Kurobe:
HERE IT COMES!
IT'S NEARLY
CAUGHT UP
TO US AGAIN!
SLAM ON THE BRAKES!
[squealing]
TAKE THIS.
YOU CAN'T GET ME.
I MISSED IT.
[gasps]
DAMN IT.
HANG IN THERE, SHION.
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
IT'LL ALL BE OVER
IN A MINUTE.
HEY,
CLASS PRESIDENT,
KEEP IN MIND
YOU ONLY HAVE ONE
BAZOOKA SHELL LEFT.
IF YOU MISS,
WE'RE SCREWED.
MAKE IT COUNT!
Gojiro, on radio:
EVERYONE, LOOK UP AHEAD.
THAT BUILDING OVER THERE
IS ABOUT TO FALL OVER.
Kurobe: I SEE IT.
THINK WE CAN
GET PAST IT?
[gasps] IS THAT...
A WATER TANK?
Gojiro: GOOD.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'LL
MAKE IT THOUGH.
HANG ON, EVERYBODY.
LET'S SEE YOU TRY
TO DODGE THIS ONE!
DIE, IBARA NARUSE!
NOW!
[gasps]
WHAT THE HELL?
JUST SOMETHING
TO COOL YOU OFF!
IS THAT...
A SPLASH OF COLD WATER.
IN YOUR DREAMS!
[laughs]
LOOKS LIKE
I WON THIS ONE,
IBARA NARUSE.
YOU CAN'T EVEN MOVE,
CAN YOU?
[laughs]
NOW TO FINISH YOU OFF
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
MISS CLASS PRESIDENT.
SO...EXHAUSTED.
[gasping]
HARUTO.
I'LL JOIN YOU SOON.
[metal clinks]
HUH?
HARUTO'S BOMB.
IT'S OVER!
[gasps]
[screams]
[grunts]
[gasps]
IBARA, ARE YOU OK?
KANON,
GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
HURRY. YOU'RE GOING
TO FALL OFF THE TRACKS.
LET ME HELP YOU.
[gasping]
IF YOU WANT
TO HELP ME,
SAVE MY SISTER
SHION.
Ibara: OK.
LIFT HER UP TO ME.
I CAN'T DO IT.
AOI.
Aoi: I HATE
THESE TWO SISTERS,
BUT--
BUT I--
I DON'T WANT
ANYONE ELSE TO DIE!
AH, SCREW IT, ANYWAY.
LET ME HELP
THE TWO OF YOU OUT.
READY?
PULL!
HEH.
THERE. SHION'S SAFE.
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN, KANON.
AFTER ALL I'VE DONE,
I HAVE NO RIGHT TO GET
ON THIS TRAIN WITH YOU.
GOODBYE,
CLASS PRESIDENT.
[gasps]
YOU IDIOT!
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
YOU'VE WON
THE BATTLE,
MISS CLASS
PRESIDENT.
JUST FORGET
ABOUT ME,
AND LET ME DIE!
[straining]
LET GO
OF MY HAND...
PLEASE.
I...
I'M DONE WITH THIS.
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
I CAN'T TAKE IT
ANYMORE!
I JUST DON'T
HAVE THE WILL
TO GO ON LIVING
IN THIS
MISERABLE WORLD.
[crying]
WHY SHOULD I
STAY ALIVE?
WHAT'S HERE FOR ME
IN THIS PLACE?
NOTHING!
NOT A SINGLE
GOOD THING.
HOW CAN I GO ON
WHEN MY LIFE HAS
NO PURPOSE?
I WISH I HAD THE ANSWERS
TO ALL OF YOUR QUESTIONS.
I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, KANON?
ONE GOOD THING DID
COME OF ALL OF THIS.
YOU AND I, WE'RE ABLE
TO BECOME FRIENDS
INSTEAD OF ENEMIES NOW.
[train clattering]
Kurobe: GENNAI,
ARE YOU STILL
WITH US?
[groans]
Gennai: HEY, KUROBE.
DID WE ALL
MAKE IT THROUGH OK?
WE'RE ALMOST
AT OUR STOP.
YOU CAN SEE THE SUNLIGHT
ON THE SKYSCRAPERS
FROM THE WINDOW.
MISS AOI,
PLEASE HELP ME
TAKE MY HELMET OFF.
[sobs]
OK, THAT SHOULD
STOP THE BLEEDING.
UH, THANK--THANK--
UH, THANK--THANK...
THANKS FOR
YOUR HELP, NARUSE.
HEH.
EH?
LOOK AT THAT.
THE CITY IS
TURNING CRIMSON.
MR. GENNAI.
[train clattering]
Aoi: GOODBYE,
AND THANK YOU.
[train horn honks]
Ibara: KANON.
THE TWO OF US
ARE GOING OUTSIDE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
WE NEED TO FIND
A GOOD SPOT
FOR THE RESCUE CHOPPER
TO LAND.
HOPEFULLY THERE'S
A GOOD OPEN AREA SOMEWHERE.
CARE TO JOIN US?
SORRY, CLASS PRESIDENT.
I HAVE MY HANDS FULL
RIGHT NOW.
I HOPE SHE'S HAVING
A NICE DREAM.
WE'LL SEE YOU
LATER THEN.
IF YOU WANT TO FIND
AN OPEN SPACE,
GO THROUGH
THE UNDERGROUND LEVEL
AND UP THE EAST EXIT.
HMM.
THE COPPELION
HAS JUST REPORTED IN
TO US, SIR.
WE'RE GOING
TO LAND EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING
IN AN OPEN AREA
IN FRONT
OF THE STATION.
HMM?
IS SOMETHING
ON YOUR MIND, SIR?
THE BABY.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
WHAT THAT CHILD'S FATE'S
GOING TO BE.
IT MIGHT FACE
MORE DEMANDING TIMES
THAN EVEN
THOSE WE FACE NOW.
I'D LIKE TO THINK
IT COULD BE BETTER,
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW.
WHAT WORLD CAN WE
GIVE THE CHILDREN?
WILL IT BE ONE
IN WHICH THEY'RE HAPPY
TO BE ALIVE?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT,
VICE PRINCIPAL?
ISN'T THAT
THE KIND OF WORLD
WE'RE WORKING
SO TIRELESSLY
TO CREATE?
HEY, AM I RIGHT,
YOU GUYS?
[crew yelling]
YEAH!
HMM. [chuckles]
[door hisses open]
[babies crying]
[all gasp]
IT'S A HEALTHY PAIR
OF TWIN BABIES.
MISS IBUKI
IS DOING FINE, TOO.
[laughs]
[all laugh]
WE DID IT, BOY!
WE DID IT!
[laughter,
crying continue]
Ibara: TAEKO.
WE SURE DID.
GOOD JOB.
YOU DID AWESOME.
I KNEW WE COULD ALL
COUNT ON YOU, TAEKO.
HMM.
[babies crying]
Taeko: I'M SO GLAD.
[radio whines]
[Gojiro cooing]
HELLO.
THIS IS GRANNY AYAME.
IS ANYONE THERE?
LOOK AT 'EM, GUYS.
COME IN.
THEY'RE MY TWINS.
[laughs]
GOOD GRIEF.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
THE ONE WHO DESERVES
THE MOST CREDIT?
[babies crying]
[chuckles]
YOU ALL DID GREAT WORK,
EVERYBODY.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[rotors whirring]
HEY, GUYS!
WE'RE DOWN HERE!
OVER HERE!
[cheering]
[sighs]
HMM?
I AM MISHIMA,
THE COMMANDER
OF THIS RESCUE TEAM.
FIRST, LET ME APOLOGIZE
FOR THE TROUBLE
OUR INEFFECTIVENESS
HAS CAUSED.
HMM. SO YOU'RE
THE ONE THEY CALL
VICE PRINCIPAL.
YOU'RE JUST
THE STRAITLACED
KIND OF MAN
I IMAGINED
YOU WOULD BE.
THIS GUY HERE IS
MY FRIEND GENNAI.
WOULD YOU
PLEASE PUT HIM
ON THE CHOPPER
WITH US?
HE DESERVES
THE OUTSIDE WORLD
AS MUCH
AS ANY OF US.
PLUS, I'M GONNA
HAVE A NEW LIFE.
I WANT TO SHOW
THE OLD GEEZER
WHAT IT CAN BE.
UNDERSTOOD.
WE'LL HELP
IN ANY WAY WE CAN.
[chuckles]
Soldier:
WE SURRENDER.
HMM?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU GUYS?
WE'RE GIVING UP AND
TURNING OURSELVES IN.
YOU CAN PUT RESTRAINTS
ON US AND TAKE US AWAY.
[groans]
AS IT HAPPENS,
WE DIDN'T BRING
ANY HANDCUFFS WITH US.
HUH?
NOW SHUT UP,
AND GET IN THE CHOPPER.
[groans]
THIS REALLY IS GOODBYE,
ISN'T IT?
AOI.
[sighs]
Aoi:
THIS IS FOR YOU.
IT'S THE PHOTO WE
ALL TOOK TOGETHER
YESTERDAY.
Gojiro:
YESTERDAY, HUH?
IT SEEMS LIKE
IT WAS AGES AGO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S BEEN JUST FOUR DAYS
SINCE THE FIRST TIME
WE MET.
IT REALLY FEELS
LIKE WE'VE BEEN
TOGETHER FOR DECADES.
TIME MOVES
IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS.
THERE HAS BEEN
A HEAVY PRICE PAID
WITH ALL THE YEARS
WE'VE LOST HERE,
BUT I FEEL
LIKE WE WERE ABLE
TO GET THEM BACK
OVER THESE LAST FOUR DAYS
IN SOME WAY.
HMM.
ME, TOO, DAD.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
I REALLY HATE
ALL THESE MUSHY MOMENTS,
SO I'M JUST
GONNA GO AHEAD
AND EXCUSE MYSELF.
SEE YOU LATER.
WHAT? THAT'S IT?
I WILL BE
ON MY WAY
AS WELL.
THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING,
MISS AOI.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
MASTER IBUKI HAS
OFFERED ME A NEW JOB
AS A BABYSITTING ROBOT
FOR HER TWINS.
MISS AOI,
FROM A BIOLOGICAL
PERSPECTIVE,
YOU ARE
A FULL-FLEDGED ADULT,
AND AS AN ADULT,
YOU MUST GET
YOUR ACT TOGETHER.
[giggles]
[sobbing]
Kurobe: I DIDN'T KNOW
ROBOTS COULD CRY.
Aoi: I WON'T EVER FORGET
WHAT YOU TAUGHT ME,
NO-SENSE,
THAT JUST
A SINGLE THOUGHT
CAN CHANGE
THE ENTIRE WORLD.
WE'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND
AS WE STRIVE TO LIVE
HERE IN THIS CITY.
I GUESS WE'D BETTER
GET GOING, TOO.
DON'T WANT TO KEEP
THAT HELICOPTER WAITING.
TAEKO, THERE'S
SOMETHING
I WOULD LIKE YOU
TO DO FOR ME.
REALLY?
WHAT IS IT,
MISS IBUKI?
I WANT YOU
TO NAME THESE TWO
BEAUTIFUL CHILDREN.
WHA? I'M SORRY,
BUT THIS IS
SO SUDDEN.
IN THAT CASE,
I'D BE HAPPY TO NAME THEM.
THIS LITTLE BOY
WILL BE RIKU,
AND THIS GIRL
SORA.
WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THOSE ARE
J.S.D.F. BRANCHES.
I THINK THOSE
ARE GREAT NAMES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
TARO?
DO YOU LIKE THEM?
AGREED. THEY'RE PERFECT.
RIKU, SORA,
TAKE A GOOD LOOK
AROUND HERE.
THIS IS WHERE
YOU WERE BORN.
GOODBYE, EVERYONE.
WE'LL MISS YOU!
TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF
AND THE BABIES!
HEY!
GOODBYE!
THANKS, GIRLS.
TAKE CARE!
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
EVERYONE.
I'LL BE THE BEST
MOTHER I CAN
TO THESE CHILDREN.
PLEASE, DO THAT.
CONSIDERING
THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
IT'S THE BEST THING
YOU COULD DO
FOR THOSE GIRLS.
HUH?
WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT,
VICE PRINCIPAL?
[both gasp]
SO THEY DIDN'T TELL YOU.
THE TRUTH IS...
RIKU AND SORA
ARE YOUR CHILDREN,
TOO, GIRLS!
Ibuki: PROMISE YOU'LL COME
AND VISIT US SOMETIME!
Ibuki:
WE'LL BE WAITING!
WE'LL ALWAYS BE WAITING
FOR YOUR RETURN!
["Bye Bye Alright"
by angela playing]
[song playing only]
[Aoi sighs]
[song continues]
I GUESS IT'S BACK
TO JUST BEING THE THREE
OF US AGAIN, HUH?
ACCORDING TO THIS,
THERE ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE SOME OTHER PEOPLE
STILL LIVING
AROUND HERE.
UH, SO WHICH WAY?
IS THIS DARN
SCHOOL FIELD TRIP
EVER GOING
TO COME TO AN END?!
[song continues]