[radio whines]
THIS IS
VICE PRINCIPAL MISHIMA.
CLEANUP CREW, COME IN.
THIS IS CLEANUP CREW.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU,
VICE PRINCIPAL?
I WANT YOU TO RENDEZVOUS
WITH THE MEDICAL UNIT
IMMEDIATELY.
THE MEDICAL UNIT?
OH, YOU MEAN
CLASS PRESIDENT
IBARA NARUSE?
ROGER THAT.
I'M ON MY WAY
RIGHT NOW.
[CAWING]
["Angel" by angela playing]
Kurobe:
SO HOW LONG UNTIL
THE SELF-DEFENSE FORCE
SHOWS UP TO RESCUE US
AND SAVE THE DAY?
Ibara:
OUR VICE PRINCIPAL
WILL BE TIED UP
FOR THREE DAYS
ON A SECURITY DETAIL
FOR A CONFERENCE.
HEH. THREE DAYS
IS NOTHING.
WE'VE BEEN ABLE
TO MANAGE BEING
STUCK IN THIS HOLE
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG,
THAT WE DON'T EXPECT
ANYONE TO COME AND
SAVE US AT THIS POINT.
STOP BEING
SO MEAN, FOREMAN.
THE GIRLS DON'T
NEED TO BE BLAMED
FOR THAT.
I KNOW THAT, IBUKI.
JUST SAYING WE HAVE
NO OTHER OPTION
BUT TO STAY HERE AND WAIT
LIKE WE ALWAYS DO.
MAYBE NOT.
IF THE FIRST DIVISION IS
SET ON FIGHTING IT OUT
WITH US,
WE'LL NEED WEAPONS
AS WELL.
[liquid bubbling]
ARE YOU FEELING OK,
MISS TAEKO?
I'M FINE, MR. GENNAI.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
YOUR GLASSES
WILL BE ON THE TABLE
FOR YOU
WHEN YOU GET UP.
IF TROUBLE
STARTS,
PROMISE YOU'LL
WAKE ME UP
IMMEDIATELY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
BECAUSE I'LL TAKE CARE
OF ANY PROBLEMS MYSELF.
[sighs]
No-sense:
THIS IS OUR ARMORY.
Ibara: WOW. YOU'VE GOT
QUITE AN ARSENAL.
Kurobe: THIS IS
MY COLLECTION.
I STARTED IT
A LONG TIME AGO
WITH SOME AIR GUNS.
HA!
NOW YOU AND YOUR
BAND OF SCHOOLGIRLS
RUN AMOK
IN THE OLD CAPITAL.
WHAT'S THIS WORLD
COMING TO?
I MEAN, AREN'T THERE
ANY MALE COPPELION
OUT THERE?
Ibara: THERE ARE BOYS
IN THE UNIT, YES.
THEN WHERE ARE THEY,
AND WHAT ARE
THEY DOING?
WELL, ONE OF THEM
IS WITH A GROUP CALLED
THE CLEANUP CREW.
THEY CLEAN UP
THE CONTAMINATION.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THEY'RE ONLY
JUST NOW STARTING
TO CLEAN UP THE MESS
IN THE OLD CAPITAL?
[laughs]
THE TRUTH IS...
EH?
WE STICK
TO OUR OWN ASSIGNMENTS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE OTHER COPPELION
ARE TOLD TO DO.
[alarm blaring]
Aoi: HUH?
[gasps]
IS THAT
AN ALARM?
WHAT'S
GOING ON?
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
IT MEANS AN INTRUDER
IS TRYING TO GO
THROUGH GATE ONE.
WAIT!
HMM. NOTHING'S
SHOWING UP ON THE
SURVEILLANCE CAMERA.
MAYBE IT'S TAEKO'S WOLF.
HE PROBABLY PICKED UP
ON HER SCENT AND THEN
FOLLOWED US HERE.
HMM? I SUPPOSE.
I'LL GO
BRING HIM INSIDE.
[gasps] UH,
SHOULDN'T YOU WAIT
FOR THE OTHERS FIRST?
HANG ON, MR. WOLF!
I'M COMING!
MR. GENNAI!
HUH?
I WAS JUST
MONITORING
THE SITUATION.
HMM?
IT'S THE FIRST DIVISION!
[gasps]
Kurobe: DID YOU SAY
THE FIRST DIVISION?
INDEED. IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE COMING
FOR US NOW.
[gasps]
WHERE'S AOI?
OH, NO! SHE RAN OUTSIDE
TO OPEN THE GATE!
Kurobe: WHAT?
SHE SHOULD BE FINE.
SHE IS A COPPELION,
AFTER ALL.
Aoi: IBARA!
[whimpers]
HURRY UP, AND COME
GET ME! IBARA, HELP!
WHAT THE HELL DOES
THAT LITTLE GIRL
THINK SHE'S DOING?
LET ME GO!
LET ME GO! HELP!
[shrieks]
Gojiro: THEY'RE
INSIDE THE GATE.
WE'RE DONE FOR.
NO, WAIT.
THEY STOPPED
IN FRONT OF THE PLANET.
Kurobe: WHAT DO
THEY WANT WITH US?
WAIT
JUST A MINUTE.
IBARA, PLEASE!
LISTEN TO ME
CAREFULLY.
THEY'RE MAKING ME
DELIVER THIS STATEMENT
IN THEIR WORDS.
PLEASE DON'T PUT UP
ANY RESISTANCE,
AND JOIN THE FIRST DIVISION
IN THEIR CRUSADE.
UH, DO WHAT?
THE SOLDIERS
OF THE FIRST DIVISION
ARE NOT OUR ENEMIES.
ALL THEY WANT TO DO IS
PROTECT THEIR TERRITORY.
IT'S WITHIN THEIR RIGHTS
TO GOVERN THE OLD CAPITAL.
[sighs]
SO YOU GUYS HAVE TO MAKE
A DECISION IMMEDIATELY.
WILL YOU COOPERATE
WITH THE FIRST DIVISION,
OR WILL...
[rifle clicks]
YOU ABANDON
THIS INNOCENT GIRL?
IT'S NOT YOU
THAT THEY'RE AFTER.
THEY'RE AFTER US,
THE COPPELION.
Gennai: HUH?
WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK THAT?
Ibara: IT WOULD EXPLAIN
WHY THEY SUDDENLY
ATTACKED YOUR VAN
OUT OF NOWHERE.
THEY KNEW
IF SOMEONE GOT HURT,
WE WOULD COME
TO THEIR RESCUE.
Gennai:
SO THAT'S IT.
THEY USED US AS BAIT.
WELL, THAT'S ODD.
WHY DO THEY
WANT YOU SO BADLY
THAT THEY'D
GO THROUGH
ALL THAT TROUBLE?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT...
IBARA!
YOU'RE NOT LEAVING ME
WITH THEM, ARE YOU?!
THAT'S ENOUGH.
WE GOT
WHAT WE CAME FOR.
WITHDRAW.
Officer: YES, SIR.
Aoi: WAIT.
NO, WAIT! WAIT!
WA-A-AIT!
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO
WITH ME?!
WHOA. THEY DIDN'T
WAIT LONG
TO RETREAT,
DID THEY?
I'M GOING AFTER THEM.
WAIT.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE
THEIR HIDEOUT IS.
I'LL TAKE YOU THERE
IF YOU
REALLY WANT TO GO.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
[radio whines]
CHANNEL TWO,
DO YOU READ ME?
COME IN, MEDICAL UNIT.
THIS IS CLEANUP CREW.
IBARA NARUSE,
ARE YOU THERE?
No-sense:
HOW DO YOU DO?
YOU HAVE REACHED
THE PLANET.
MISS IBARA
AND HER PARTY
DEPARTED 5 MINUTES,
38 SECONDS AGO.
THE FIRST DIVISION'S HIDEOUT
IS HERE IN THIS PARK?
TAKE A LOOK
FOR YOURSELF.
COME ON.
[grunts]
IT'S JUST A MASSIVE
PILE OF OLD JUNK.
THAT'S WHERE
THE GHOSTS HANG OUT.
THEY'VE BEEN
BUILDING IT UP
GRADUALLY
OVER MANY YEARS.
[gasps]
HEY!
Ibara:
STOP RIGHT THERE!
HMM?
ONE MOVE, AND I'LL
SHOOT YOU DOWN.
HEH.
IBARA, YOU GOTTA
GET AWAY!
HUH?
THESE GUYS
ARE INSANE,
AND THEY'RE
NOT AFRAID
OF BEING SHOT!
THREATS LIKE
THAT WON'T DO US
ANY GOOD AT ALL!
SHOOT ME.
[gasping]
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
LITTLE GIRL?
I'M UNARMED.
GO RIGHT AHEAD
AND KILL ME.
[grunts]
AH, SHIT.
[soldiers grunting]
Kurobe: WHY
DIDN'T YOU SHOOT,
YOU IDIOT?
STOP!
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
HUH?
WELL, WELL.
SEEMS LIKE
THE CLASS PRESIDENT
NEEDS HELP.
WHO ARE YOU?
OH, HEY. IT'S THE GUY
FROM THE CLEANUP CREW.
OPEN FIRE!
[chuckles]
WHA--
IT'S OVER.
FOR YOU.
[screams]
Kurobe: HEY, KID!
OPEN UP
THIS DANG THING!
LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE!
Coppelion:
AOI FUKASAKU,
OVER HERE!
Kurobe: GET YOUR ASS
I'M SAVED.
THE HOSTAGE
IS GETTING AWAY!
[gasps]
[screams]
RUN FASTER,
LITTLE GIRL!
THEY'RE COMING
AFTER YOU!
COME ON.
I GOT YA!
GRAB MY HAND!
COME ON!
[Aoi screams]
Kurobe:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[distant chatter]
HARUTO!
OH. DIDN'T YOU
HEAR THE BELL?
[gasps]
[metal clangs]
[groans]
Haruto:
DON'T BREAK IT.
YOUR ROCK-HARD HEAD
MIGHT SPLIT
THE CARRIER IN TWO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HARUTO KUROSAWA
FROM
THE CLEANUP CREW?
I RECEIVED AN URGENT CALL
FROM THE VICE PRINCIPAL
ORDERING US TO ASSIST
YOUR MEDICAL UNIT.
OH, YOU'RE AWAKE NOW.
I JUST WOKE UP.
GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
SORRY ABOUT THAT
BACK THERE.
WE WERE A LITTLE LATE
COMING TO YOUR RESCUE.
NO, IT WAS MY FAULT
FOR RUNNING OFF ON MY OWN.
OH. WERE YOU
ABLE TO GET AOI
BACK HERE ALL RIGHT?
Kurobe: WE HAD
TO LEAVE HER BEHIND.
WHAT?
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
I CAN'T BE HELD HOSTAGE
BY THESE MANIACS!
MORONS!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
WHY DO I ALWAYS
HAVE BAD LUCK?!
[groans]
EH, IT AIN'T
MY FAULT,
SISTER.
IT WAS HIS
AWFUL DRIVING
THAT MADE ME
DROP HER.
WE HAVE
TO RESCUE HER.
SETTLE DOWN THERE,
NARUSE.
I STUCK A TRANSMITTER
ON AOI FUKASAKU
THAT'LL LET US DETECT
HER LIFE SIGNS.
ARE YOU GUYS ABLE...
Haruto: IT HAS A SENSOR
THAT SENDS A SIGNAL
AS LONG AS SHE'S ALIVE.
WITH IT, WE'LL BE ABLE
TO TRACK WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
HOLD ON. YOU MEAN
YOU LEFT AOI BEHIND
JUST SO YOU
COULD MONITOR
THE MOVEMENTS
THE FIRST DIVISION
MAKES?
DOESN'T IT
BOTHER YOU...
HUH?
NOT BEING ABLE TO KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT
THE FIRST DIVISION
WANTS WITH US?
THAT'S NO REASON
TO SACRIFICE A FRIEND.
DID I SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT SACRIFICING?
THEY'LL KEEP HER ALIVE
SINCE SHE'S
USEFUL TO THEM.
HUH?
JUST WAIT AND SEE.
THE EXPLOSION EARLIER
RENDERED THEIR BASE
IN THAT MOUNTAIN OF JUNK
COMPLETELY USELESS.
THEY CAN'T STAY THERE
ANYMORE,
SO THEY'RE GONNA HAVE
TO MOVE ALONG.
WE'LL BE ABLE
TO GRAB AOI FUKASAKU
JUST AFTER THEY
MAKE THEIR MOVE.
SO ALL WE CAN DO
IS SIT AROUND HERE
AND WAIT
UNTIL THE GHOSTS
DECIDE THAT THEY'RE
READY TO MOVE ON?
PRECISELY.
I JUST FEEL SO BAD
FOR AOI
TRAPPED ALL ALONE
AND CRYING.
[shrieks]
[laughs]
THIS RICE BALL
IS SO YUMMY!
MISO SOUP, PLEASE!
I'M NOT SURE
THIS FIRE IS
SUCH A GREAT IDEA.
WON'T THEY BE ABLE
TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE WE ARE?
I DOUBT IT.
THE FIRST DIVISION
HAS PROBABLY GOT
THEIR HANDS FULL
PREPARING TO MOVE OUT.
I CAN KEEP A LOOKOUT
FOR NOW.
YOU SHOULD GO
GET SOME REST, NARUSE.
HEH. MY WOUNDS
HAVE HEALED UP ALREADY.
DROP THE ACT.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE BEEN
A LOUSY LIAR.
WHILE YOU WERE ASLEEP,
I CHECKED YOU OVER
FROM HEAD TO TOE.
THESE PAST FEW DAYS HAVE
COMPLETELY WORN YOU OUT.
EVEN WITH YOUR
RECUPERATIVE ABILITIES,
YOU STILL COULD USE
A FULL DAY'S REST
TO RECOVER.
UM, CHECKED
HEAD TO TOE
IN MY SLEEP?
I'M JUST SAYING
THEY KEEP TALKING
ABOUT RESCUING US
BECAUSE OF THE ACCIDENT,
BUT OUR LIVES
SUCKED ALREADY
WITH THE RECESSION
GOING ON AND ALL THAT.
BUT HERE, WE DON'T HAVE
TO WORK OR PAY TAXES
OR DO ANY OF THAT
TROUBLESOME STUFF
LIKE WE USED TO.
[sighs] I DON'T
EVER WANT TO RETURN
TO THAT KIND
OF B.S. SOCIETY.
[sighs] KUROBE,
TRY TO LOOK AT IT
LIKE THIS.
THOSE CHILDREN BEAR
A HEAVY RESPONSIBILITY
FORCED ONTO THEM
AT BIRTH.
THEY WILL BE BOUND
BY THAT CURSE
UNTIL THEY COMPLETE
THEIR MISSION.
WOW.
THE STARS
LOOK AMAZING
OUT HERE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY
YOU CAN SEE THEM SO WELL
IN THE OLD CAPITAL, NARUSE?
HMM?
THERE ARE NO LIGHTS
FOR MILES AROUND HERE.
THE TECHNOLOGICAL SPIRIT
THAT BUILT THIS CITY
ULTIMATELY DESTROYED IT.
AREN'T HUMAN BEINGS
THE MOST PITIFUL CREATURES?
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHAT SORT OF WORK
DOES THE CLEANUP CREW
DO, HARUTO?
[beeping]
THE TRANSMITTER'S
MOVING.
WHAT?
THE FIRST DIVISION
IS MAKING ITS MOVE NOW.
NARUSE, YOU READY?
YES.
Kurobe: OK,
IS EVERYBODY ON BOARD?
WHY ARE YOU DRAGGING
ME ALONG WITH YOU?
WE NEED MANPOWER,
SO SUCK IT UP
THERE, GENNAI.
STEP ON IT,
HARUTO.
LET'S GET
THIS THING
MOVING.
HOLD IT,
YOU TWO.
SEE THIS?
Kurobe: IT'S A MAP
OF ALL THE ZONES,
THE HEAVILY
CONTAMINATED AREAS.
THOSE ARE ALL ZONES?
IT'S OK FOR YOU TWO,
BUT IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
FOR US ORDINARY HUMANS.
WE'LL NEED TO DETOUR
AROUND THE ZONE
TO CATCH THOSE GHOSTS.
MAYBE HARUTO AND I
SHOULD BE THE ONES
TO GO OUT THERE.
YOU KIDDING?
I'M NOT MISSING THIS.
Gennai: THE FOREMAN
THINKS HE'S SOME
KIND OF JARHEAD.
Haruto: THE FIRST DIVISION
IS HEADED
DIRECTLY NORTHWEST.
I GUESS THEY FIGURED OUT
WHERE THEY WANT TO GO.
CAN YOU TELL FROM
THE LOOKS OF THINGS
WHERE WE MIGHT BE?
IS THIS
A TRAIN STATION?
Kurobe:
IT IS.
A TRAIN, HUH?
WHAT A WASTE.
BY NOW,
IT MUST BE A HEAP
OF RUSTED METAL.
Gennai:
NOT AT ALL.
HUH?
Gennai:
WE WERE USING IT
UNTIL JUST RECENTLY
TO TRANSPORT
ALL SORTS OF GOODS
FROM THE CENTER
OF THE OLD CAPITAL.
REALLY?
IT WAS STILL RUNNING?
SURE WAS.
WE RAN POWER LINES
FROM THE HYDROELECTRIC PLANT
TO KEEP THE TRAIN
OPERATIONAL.
HMM, BUT IT'S NOT
UP AND RUNNING
ANYMORE.
THE POWER LINE
HAS A BREAK SOMEWHERE,
BUT THE ZONE
IS PREVENTING US
FROM DOING REPAIRS.
DON'T BE FRIGHTENED.
[gasps]
WE'RE JUST GOING
TO NEED YOUR HELP
A LITTLE LATER.
ONCE WE'RE DONE, I PROMISE
I'LL SEND YOU BACK HOME.
[thinking]
HE'S SO LYING.
I'M SO GOING
TO BE KILLED.
Haruto: THE FIRST DIVISION
MADE A RIGHT TURN.
THE ROAD LEADS
TO A MASSIVE ZONE.
Kurobe:
THAT ONE'S NOT
SO DANGEROUS.
SEE? IT SHOWS
IT'S LOW-LEVEL HERE.
LOW-LEVEL?
IT'S NOT AS BAD
AS OTHER ZONES,
BUT IT'S
GETTING WORSE.
SOMETHING OR SOMEONE
HAS GOT BE THE CAUSE
OF THE INCREASE
IN POLLUTION OVER THERE.
SO WHAT'S
IN THAT AREA, ANYWAY?
I COULD TELL YOU,
BUT WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TAKE A LOOK
FOR YOURSELF?
Ibara: WHAT ARE
ALL THOSE POOLS?
IT'S A WATER
TREATMENT PLANT.
BACK IN THE DAY,
THESE SUPPLIED
EVERYONE'S
TAP WATER.
NOWADAYS,
THEY'RE FULL OF
CONTAMINATED WATER.
[gasps]
HUH?
WE SPOTTED
THE FIRST DIVISION.
BRING THEM UP SLOWLY.
CAREFUL.
WHAT IN THE HELL?
THEY'RE LOADING
THOSE YELLOW BARRELS
INTO A TRUCK.
Ibara:
THAT'S LOW-LEVEL WASTE.
Kurobe: WAIT.
THAT COULD MEAN
THAT BARRELS LIKE THOSE
ARE AT THE BOTTOM
OF ALL THESE POOLS.
SO WHAT'S
OUR PLAN NOW?
OUR FIRST PRIORITY
IS GETTING AOI.
NOT SO FAST.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"NOT SO FAST"?
THINGS WERE JUST
STARTING TO GET GOOD.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
AN EXPLOSION!
THE ENEMY'S ATTACKING!
[gasps]
IT'S IBARA.
HMM.
HEY, GUYS!
OVER HERE!
AFTER HIM!
HERE THEY COME!
COME ON,
YOU GHOSTS!
[footsteps]
GOOD.
THE DIVERSION'S
WORKING.
NOW TO CLEAN UP.
HARUTO, WAIT.
DON'T DO THAT.
IF YOU SHOOT THEM,
THEY'LL DIE.
THAT'S JUST
HOW IT WORKS.
YOU MEAN YOU'RE
TRYING TO KILL
THOSE PEOPLE?
YOU KNOW WE'RE PUPPETS,
NARUSE.
BEING NICE TO HUMANS
WON'T BRING US
ANYTHING IN RETURN.
JUST LEAVE
THE DIRTY WORK
TO THE CLEANUP CREW,
ALL RIGHT?
HARUTO!
ENEMY SPOTTED!
[gunfire]
IT'S THE ENEMY!
[groans]
STUPID HARUTO.
ARE THE BARRELS
LOADED YET?
THE ENEMY'S FIRING
ON US! RETURN FIRE!
COMMANDER,
I THINK WE
SHOULD LEAVE.
AGREED.
IBARA!
HUH?
COME SAVE ME!
I'M OVER HERE!
HEY, SHUT UP!
Aoi: IBARA, HELP ME!
IBARA!
HANG IN THERE, AOI.
[grunts]
[gasping]
I SAW THROUGH
YOUR EVERY MOVE,
BECAUSE YOU AND I
ARE BOTH THE SAME.
WE TRAINED
TO PROTECT THIS COUNTRY,
YOU AND I...
ARE NOTHING ALIKE!
[coughs]
HE'S NOT WEARING
AN OXYGEN TANK.
DO YOU GET IT NOW?
WE'RE NOT
AFRAID OF DEATH.
YOUR MISSION SEEMS TO BE
TO RESCUE PEOPLE.
IN THAT CASE, YOU NEED
TO LEARN MORE ABOUT PEOPLE.
IN SOME CASES,
HUMANITY CAN BE
EASILY LOST.
[laughing]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
TO MY EYES, YOU LOOK
LIKE A NORMAL HUMAN.
HMM.
PLEASE STOP
ALL OF THIS.
LET US HELP YOU.
NOW FIRE
AT THE TWO OF US!
NARUSE.
GET IN, KID!
DID THE SHELL
HIT THE TARGET?
CONFIRM.
EXCUSE ME.
I NEED TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
HURRY. GET OUT OF HERE.
HUH?
KEEP GOING FORWARD.
NARUSE'S
AROUND SOMEWHERE.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE WALKING, GIRL!
HAVE YOU SEEN NARUSE?
[sniffles]
[crying]
HUH?
EH?
[gasps]
Haruto: NARUSE!
["Tokumade" by angela playing]
Aoi: RESUSCITATION...
A LIFE WORTH SAVING...
THIRD-YEAR STUDENTS...
POINTLESS WORDS...
NEXT-GENERATION ENERGY...
THE SOUND OF A BEATING HEART...
THE YELLOW CAKE...
NEXT TIME ON "COPPELION"...
HARUTO.