It's tilting!
We should've evacuated
the city earlier.
[PROFESSOR] Do you understand
what I've done, Kyotaro?
I've put us all
on the same page.
No matter how much
you may fight for them,
they will never consider
you their ally.
Give it up and
join us, Kyotaro.
[PEGGY squeals]
Rinka, no!
[CROWD gasping]
[PEGGY squealing]
[KYOTARO yells]
[PROFESSOR cackles]
[CROWD screams]
Rinka!
This is how it all begins.
We've sown the seeds to
cultivate a better world.
We're now live at the scene.
where only moments ago,
this tanker was
dropped on Tokyo Tower.
Although details are slim,
an unknown esper group
is believed
to be responsible
for the carnage.
[YODANI grunts]
It looks like it's all finally
hitting the fan, doesn't it?
The time of the great
trial is upon us.
[MALE OFFICER 6A]
Please hurry, folks.
We need to evacuate the area!
[PEGGY sqeaking]
[RINKA gasps]
Kyotaro!
[KYOTARO]
Don't worry about me.
Kuroi needs your help more.
[gasps] Oh. Yeah!
[RINKA] I promise I'll be
back as soon as I can, okay?
[PEGGY]
Ah...
[RINKA]
Over here!
[MALE EMT 6A]
What happened to her?
[RINKA] I don't know,
but it looks like something
hit her in the shoulder.
We'll get her all
fixed up. Hey! Wait!
[RINKA] There's a boy
who's hurt back there!
I'm gonna go get him!
[RINKA]
Hang on, Kyotaro!
[RINKA gasps]
[MINAMI] You've poisoned
his mind, you know.
He'll never come to his senses
while you're still
in the picture.
And what is that even
supposed to mean?
Just get the hell
away from him, okay!
You and your father have put
him through more than enough!
[MINAMI]
He's mine.
[RINKA]
Huh?
You've put him through
enough. Not me.
[MOTHER 6A]
Help... Please...
Can...
Can anyone hear me?
[RINKA]
I'm coming, ma'am!
Just try to stay calm!
[groans]
Hey! C'mere! Gimme a hand!
I will be taking Kyotaro back.
No way!
[MOTHER 6A] Please don't leave.
Rescue my child.
[RINKA]
Drop him!
[MINAMI]
You'll have to take him from me.
But you will fail.
And in the meantime,
they'll die.
[MOTHER 6A]
Please. I'm begging you!
[RINKA] It's all right!
I'm gonna get you out!
Save my baby, first!
[RINDOU yelling]
[RINKA]
Dad!
We've got wounded here!
Move your asses!
You're not hurt
are ya? You're okay?
[RINKA]
Mm-hm.
[RINDOU]
How 'bout the rest?
[RINKA] Kuroi's getting help.
But Kyotaro...
[PEGGY whining]
She took him.
[MALE OFFICER 6A]
Is anyone in there?
[MALE OFFICER 6B]
Yell if you can hear me!
[MALE OFFICER 6C] Over here!
He's pinned under a big piece!
We've gotta help them.
Our powers! We have
them for a reason!
[MALE OFFICER 6A] Damn it all!
There's no way we can lift this!
[RINKA]
I'll check it out for you!
[RINKA] Found one!
There's a guy two meters down!
He's still alive!
We're on it.
We need a crane here,
right now! E.T.A?
[RINDOU] Pull 'em out already!
This ain't easy!
[MALE LEADER 6A]
Yes'sir!
[MALE OFFICER 6B]
Hey, what the hell?
Aren't they the same kind of
freaks that did this?
Espers or whatever
they're called?
[MALE LEADER 6A]
Who gives a damn?
Those two are working
their asses off
to help us out. Freaks or not,
they're fine by me.
[RINKA]
Watch out, guys!
[RINKA gasps]
[sobs]
[MALE EMT 6B]
Hurry! We found another one!
[RINDOU]
Listen to me.
I know she was up
on that ship, but...
My daughter ain't no
damned terrorist.
I'd like to question her,
but I got bigger
fish to fry.
So you trust us, is that
what you're tellin' me?
Yeah, maybe. All I know.
You're more help to me out here
than stuck in some cell.
So, the White Girl's your kid.
Ain't that some shit.
[FEMALE REPORTER 1A]
We bring you this live update.
It's been ten days now since
the brazen attack by espers
here at Tokyo Tower.
42 people reported
dead in the carnage.
And over 200 were
seriously injured.
If they think we're just
going to roll over like a dog,
then they've got a
big surprise coming!
Once I'm elected, I'm gonna
nip this in the bud!
[AYUMU]
Yeah.
Rinka! Didn't ya hear?
There's this crazy new
invention called summer break.
[RINKA] Very funny.
I was absent on exam day.
[ASHITABA]
That sucks.
Ya hear about the attack?
It's on the news,
like, non-stop.
Ya mean those freaks
droppin' that boat?
[RUU]
Yup.
[ASHITABA]
Ugh. I'm, like, so over it!
My parents refuse
to shut up about it.
[HARUMOA] Weird powers,
though! W.T.F. right?
I'm not saying that I did it.
but if you go online,
you can find a lot
of gruesome pics
of the dead bodies.
[HARUMOA]
Aw, nasty!
[ASHITABA]
Oh yeah, so spill it Rinka.
How's it going with you
and that upperclassman?
Hey, Rinka!
You good with cold
noodles for lunch?
[PEGGY squeaks]
You are such a sad-sack.
Just give it a rest.
Dammit!
Why'd the AC have'ta take
a dump during a heat-wave?
I'm trying to freakin' heal!
Yeah, well,
the AC at the hospital
works just fine.
What? I'm a notorious
thief, dumbass!
Hospitals are Cop Central,
they woulda found me
in no time at all!
Hm?
Time out! I was wearing that!
Well, you're sweaty.
Why're you so mad?
What the hell? You stripped me!
Yeah-- It's bath time.
Uh...
[RINKA]
You heard me.
Now peel off
those sweaty shorts.
[KUROI]
That is not gonna happen, Rinka!
You can wash my hair,
if you wanna help!
[RINKA]
So, is it too hot?
[KUROI] Nah, it's fine. Y'know,
this sucks pretty damn hard.
First I get shot by
my own little sister,
then my rival drags my
unconscious ass to safety.
Kyotaro saved you.
Saved both of us.
You're an idiot if you
think he's dead, Rinka.
I promise you,
he's alive and kicking.
If she had wanted to kill him,
she could've sealed
the deal right there.
Why take him along, y'know?
[yells]
Been a while since
we sparred huh?
Couple o' years
at the very least!
[yells]
Somebody's out for blood.
You ain't holdin' back. Good!
[RINKA, RINDOU grunting]
You've completely poisoned
his mind, you know.
[yells]
[RINKA]
It's my fault. I let it happen.
The Professor told me
he was gonna do something
and I just stuck
my head in the sand.
I couldn't even save Kyotaro.
[RINKA] When's it gonna sink in
I'm not some superhero?
I'm just a kid who's
in way over her head.
It's okay, doll.
This ain't even
your fight and still,
you're doin' everything ya can.
[RINKA]
You don't get it, Dad!
They could do it
all again tomorrow.
[RINKA] And I'd still be
just as powerless to stop them.
[YODANI] If you honestly
believe that, then why even
bother worrying your pretty
little head about it, huh?
[YODANI laughs]
[yelps]
[RINKA]
Dad!
[gasps]
[RINKA yelps]
[YODANI laughs]
Not much of a fighter,
but you do have other assets!
[RINKA yelps]
Gimme back my bra!
[RINDOU]
Whoa, down, girl!
That panda's a pal o' mine.
[YODANI] Well, it's been
quite a while now.
Hasn't it, Urushiba?
[RINDOU]
It has, Roshi.
Huh?
You mean you actually
know this pervert furry?
That's putting it lightly.
The man inside
this suit taught me
everything I know
about martial arts.
He's my sensei.
[RINKA]
What?!
[RINDOU]
Whoa! You're an esper, too?
It's like an epidemic.
[YODANI] Turns out an old
panda can learn new tricks.
Mine is to view events
from a remote distance.
So, uh, what's with the mascot?
No idea.
[YODANI] Every now and then,
I get a glimpse of you all,
and that "Professor" fella.
[RINKA]
Then you can find Kyotaro!
[YODANI]
Don't get to pick what I see.
But ya don't exactly
need precognition
to know what's comin'.
[YODANI] People are sad
and scared these days.
Can't blame 'em.
There's a hell of
a darkness prowling
the edges of the city
right now, waiting to strike.
Sticking your head in
the sand like an ostrich
won't help any.
The boogeyman's lurking
out there all the same.
We've got villains.
So let's make sure,
we have enough heroes
to give the Professor
and his the what-for.
Of course, it's up
to each of you
whether you lend a hand or not.
I know you've
scuffled with 'em a bit,
but the real fight is coming,
and it's gonna be a doozy.
So, then.
Do you have the backbone
to train with me
and tread the hero's path?
[piano playing]
[PROFESSOR]
Does it still pain you?
[gasps]
[PROFESSOR]
The injury you sustained
while battling the White Girl?
Of course it doesn't.
In the big picture,
this wound is nothing.
We allowed so many
people to die, Father.
[PROFESSOR]
Minami.
Have you begun to regret
this life we've chosen?
[MINAMI] Of course not.
You'll never be alone.
I promise you that.
[PROFESSOR]
I see.
[KYOTARO grunting]
Rinka. Please...
[MINAMI]
You're awake.
[KYOTARO]
Minami!
[MINAMI]
Don't bother.
Father's used his power
to clip your wings.
[PROFESSOR]
My fellow espers!
Your powers are not
a burden, but a gift to you!
Now is the time to rise up
and use those gifts!
Yours is a tremendous power
they cannot hope to rival!
This little viral plague
has been their call to arms.
The number of esper-related
crimes and accidents
has shot through
the goddamn roof.
Those bastards really
kicked the hornet's nest,
didn't they?
The brass is going in circles
chasing their tails.
They can't decide.
But some of 'em would be
just as happy to chuck
the whole damn lot of ya in jail
and fire the key off into space.
[RINDOU grunts]
[NABESHIMA]
How's your kid doing?
How's she coping
with all this?
She sure as hell ain't
runnin' away from it anymore.
[RINKA panting]
Hey, uh, I do get to
fight eventually, right?
[YODANI] Where's this
question coming from?
Well, so far, all you've
had me do is cardio.
[pants]
[YODANI] Hm. I've seen noses
that run faster than you, kid.
[RINKA]
Bite me!
It's too hot. No one
can move in this heat.
[YODANI]
Panda boob fist!
[RINKA screams]
[RINKA] Stop it,
you perverted old creep!
That's sexual harassment!
[YODANI laughs]
[YODANI]
You jiggle even more
when you swing around
blindly like that.
Huh?
[YODANI]
Double panda boob fist!
[RINKA screams]
[MURASAKI laughs]
[MURASAKI]
Awesome! I got it right!
[YODANI] "Awesome," eh?
Piss-poor, in my opinion.
Huh?
[YODANI]
Strengthening your memory
is not the point
of this exercise.
Learn to use your psychometry,
and you'll solve 'em all
by touching a single card and
sifting through its history.
Now, focus, girlie! Focus!
Yessir.
[PEGGY squeaks]
[RINDOU grunting]
[RINKA yelping]
Um. I kinda feel like
I should be getting
some esper training too, y'know.
[YODANI]
Oh, quit your squawkin' already.
All you need to worry about
is staying inside that circle!
[RINKA] But, look how
small the circle is!
How do you expect
me to have any room
to maneuver in here?
[YODANI] Wouldn't be
a problem if you weren't
so in love with kicking.
Huh?
[YODANI] The combat training
you're gonna receive
is the same I taught your father
and the other police cadets
at the academy back
in the good ol' days
before my retirement.
It's a counter-riot
technique I've named C.P.C!
Close. Panda. Combat!
[grunting]
[YODANI] Punching and kicking
may seem effective,
but all they do is
anger your target.
It's better to counter
the enemy's moves
and throw off their
center of gravity.
Grapple them into your hold
and then push, pull, and twist
to take 'em down with
the least amount of fuss.
And once you've
got your opponent
firmly on the ground,
that's all she wrote.
Man. That's boring!
[YODANI]
You sure are mouthy, eh?
[RINDOU]
Master Roshi.
I'm gonna be late for work
if I don't get going,
but I'll be back in a bit.
[YODANI]
I see.
Not that you've earned it, but
I guess you can take a break.
Dang. I am so wiped out!
Hey, mind if I
steal ya for a sec?
[RINKA]
So, how's the shoulder?
[KUROI] Better, but it's sure
taking its sweet-ass time.
Startin' to get
restless, y'know?
[RINKA]
I bet.
[KUROI] Look, Rinka, you've got
a really shitty attitude.
[RINKA]
Huh?
[KUROI]
Seriously.
Just watching you practice
even pisses me off.
I've seen a lot of
people come around
who think the same way you do.
The ones who always think
it's best to avoid a fight
and then by the time they
embrace it as an option,
it's practically too late.
Most people are like that.
[KUROI] That kinda
thinkin's gonna get you
straight up killed next time.
[KUROI] Do this for real,
or walk away.
I hope you know losing you would
break your old man's heart.
[RINKA]
Yeah, I know that.
[YOUNG KUROI whimpering]
[KUROI]
I've lived like a stray dog
ever since I was
just a little kid.
Watching you and your dad,
it makes me feel kinda
peaceful or some shit.
Having a family seems
like a sweet deal.
[KUROI]
Oh, hey!
When this is all said and done,
we still gotta fight again!
[RINKA]
Huh?
[KUROI]
You heard me!
I'd practice my ass off
if I were you.
Just you and me, girl!
No holds barred!
[RINDOU]
Hey, Rinka.
[RINKA]
What's up?
Detective Nabeshima
dropped by work today
and gave this to me.
Asked me to pass it onto you.
[RINDOU] I guess they must've
found it when they were
clearing out the rubble
around Tokyo Tower.
[RINKA] This is it.
I have to get stronger!
I couldn't stop
the Professor last time.
But next time will be different!
Either I stop him,
or I die trying.
[RINKA]
Master Roshi!
I know that I wasn't
ready before,
but I am now if you're
still willing to teach me.
[YODANI] Sounds to me like
you've found your resolve.
So from here on out,
I won't take any more excuses!
Right!
[YODANI]
This here is Ayumu Ozora.
He's a middle-schooler,
and one of my regular students.
And as of now,
he will also be
your sparring partner.
[AYUMU] What? You can't
just volunteer me!
I've got summer school,
Master Roshi!
[YODANI]
Oh, c'mon, now! Be a pal!
I'm startin' to get the feeling
he didn't come here willingly.
[RINKA] Yeah, poor
little guy. And that afro!
[AYUMU growls]
[groans]
It's not an afro!
It's just naturally curly!
So, you wanna fight?
Then show me whatcha got!
[PEGGY]
Scene 07, "Girls in the Rain."