Minami.
[KAKUNOSHIN]
I'll take care of the peons.
Works for me.
This time you stay dead!
[yells]
[YODANI]
Good luck, Rinka. Hm?
[YODANI] Ugh...!
[YODANI] That's the guy!
He's the one keeping
the building in the air!
Open fire!
[YODANI] What?!
[KAKUNOSHIN laughs]
You must be unaware
that I'm the one
who's been training Minami and
the others for years now...
Do you really think bullets
are enough to stop me?
Pure absurdity!
[YODANI] Wonderful. He must
be a master of cheegong.
[KAKUNOSHIN yells]
[MALE OFFICERS, SORIMACHI grunt]
Why the hell
won't you just die?!
[RINKA yells]
[RINKA grunts]
[RINKA]
Tell me where Kyotaro is!
What have you done with him?!
Hm! What do you think?
How else could I
remove him from you...?
[RINKA huffs]
[MINAMI] Other than
to remove his head?
Don't lie to me!
He was a part of your family.
I know you couldn't
do that to him!
You know nothing about me!
And what do you care, anyway?!
You're the one
who always dragged him
into danger without thinking!
[gasps, yells]
--[MINAMI yells]
--[RINKA screams]
[MINAMI] How could you
possibly understand?!
[MINAMI] You think you know
what we've been through?
You couldn't even imagine
the pain we've suffered.
[MINAMI] You don't know
anything about us!
[yells]
[screams]
[MINAMI] It's your fault.
You stole Kyotaro away from me.
[RINKA screams]
[MINAMI] This world is sick...
Humanity is a plague...
That must be eradicated.
[RINKA] You have to know
that's impossible.
Hating people
and holding grudges...
the need to fight...
and even sometimes
falling in love.
Espers are part of humanity!
Don't you see?!
You can't change that!
[RINKA]
Nothing will ever change.
If you succeed...
If you manage to create
this new world
you won't shut up about...
it'll be the exact same!
[RINKA] Kyotaro was
trying to help you!
He was trying to
save you from making
such a meaningless sacrifice!
[MINAMI gasps]
[RINKA]
If you cared about him,
why was it so hard for you
to just believe him?!
If you had listened...
If you could have
only believed in him...
Everything could have
turned out so differently...
We could've learned
to live together.
If you're not gonna fight me,
you're just asking to die!
I won't let you have him...
no matter what.
[gasps]
--[MINAMI grunts]
--[RINKA] Aah!
He can try to fight me
all he wants...
but I'll drag him
kicking and screaming
to the new world with me.
[RINKA]
He is alive... I knew it...
I knew she couldn't kill him.
[yells]
[RINKA grunts]
Damn you!
[RINKA]
Skull Crushing... Psy-Kick!
[KAKUNOSHIN bellows]
[SORIMACHI grunts, groans]
[YODANI] Mm?
[FEMALE OFFICER 2A,
NABESHIMA groan]
[YODANI] What the hell,
are you two crazy?!
[FEMALE OFFICER 2A,
NABESHIMA groan]
[KAKUNOSHIN grunts]
[SORIMACHI yells, groans]
[YODANI] Pompadour! Hm?
[grunts]
[YODANI] It's lookin'
like this is the end.
[SUKESABURO] Hm?
[weapon clanks]
[SUKESABURO] Uh! Hm.
[AYUMU whimpers]
Uh!
[MURASAKI, PEGGY,
KUROI, and AYUMU yell]
Reverse, Peggy!
Aaah!
[MURASAKI, KUROI,
and AYUMU yell]
[groans]
[SUKESABURO] You may
be able to see the future,
but it looks like you've
run out of time, afro.
Ayumu!
It's not a freakin' afro.
[SUKESABURO grunts]
[MURASAKI panting]
[SUKESABURO] Uh!
[AYUMU]
I've just got curly hair!
[SUKESABURO groans]
[MURASAKI quavering exhale]
[YODANI]
Get out of here!
You're no match
for this guy, just run!
[KUROI]
Sounds like a challenge.
And I've been lookin'
for a reason to show off.
I didn't just disappear these
last few months for nothin'.
[yells]
[KAKUNOSHIN grunts]
[MURASAKI gasps]
[KUROI] Hah. Funny what
a little training can do.
Now stay dead.
[YODANI] Everyone,
grab hold of something!
There's nothing
holding us up now!
[low rumbling]
[KUROI groans]
No way!
[RINKA] Dad!
[growls, bellows]
Stop, you bastard!
We're not falling.
Does this mean that...
we're saved?
[RINDOU groans]
Bleh-ah-aah!
[RINDOU breathes heavily]
Heh. Freakin' miracle.
There's more injured inside!
[MALE OFFICER 12A]
We'll get help!
[REIA] Ayumu!
[gasps]
[AYUMU] Mom!
[REIA] I'm so sorry...
Please forgive me!
[AYUMU] It's okay, Mom...
I love you.
[REIA sniffs]
[MURASAKI gasps]
Wait, isn't that...?
That kabuki creep
was holding this.
[gasps]
[YODANI] Hey, Rinka!
[RINKA] Roshi!
[YODANI]
I'm so glad you're safe!
The Professor?
Was he in the building?
[YODANI] They escaped
before we came down...
I can't get a read on them,
so I doubt they're
anywhere even close to here.
I figured as much.
[MURASAKI] Rinka!
They aren't finished yet!
--[RINKA gasps]
--[YODANI] Huh?
[MURASAKI] This was nothing!
It was just a distraction!
The Professor plans
to spread the fish
throughout the city!
He's gonna use transmission
waves to do it!
There's only
one place they can be.
[YODANI]
The Tokyo Sky Tree!
[KYOTARO gasps]
Whoa... What the hell's
wrong with the sky?
[YODANI] They've played
their winning hand.
The Professor's
greatest weakness
was his small number of espers.
But he's tipped the balance
in his favor now...
No matter how many
laws they pass,
the government will never
be able to control this.
We're witnessing the birth
of an entire race of espers...
and they'll descend upon Tokyo
like a plague of locusts.
--[MINAMI] Hm!
--[MURASAKI, RINKA, YODANI] Hm?
[MINAMI] Then you
recognize that we've won...
It won't be long before the
espers take over this city.
You're done...
And there's nothing you
can do to protect anyone now.
[RINKA] Get back here!
[MURASAKI] Are you okay?
You feel up to lending me
your wings, Peggy?
[PEGGY squeals]
[YODANI]
Don't do it, Rinka...
You haven't stopped fighting
since we got sprung
and you're injured...
You are well past your limit.
[RINKA]
I can still do it... I can!
[KUROI]
Just to be clear...
You do have
a better plan than
rushing in headfirst
and dying again, right?
What? How long've
you been around?
Don't change the subject...
You better not get offed.
Your dad's been through
enough already.
I know he has.
Is that why
you're tagging along?
Are you trying to protect me
to protect my dad?
Uh. Let's just say it's
cuz I'm a good person.
Or some bullshit.
Just do me one favor
in exchange, okay?
[KUROI] Tell your dad
how awesome I am.
[RINKA] Hm!
[gasps] Ah-haaa!
[gasps]
[KUROI gasps]
Holy crap...
Kinda feels like we're swimming
more than it does flying.
[gasps]
[RINKA] If Kyotaro
were in my shoes,
I know that he'd
keep going no matter
how hopeless things look.
[KUROI] Mm.
Hm!
You've got yourself
a new home, pal!
[crunch]
[cell phone rings]
We've got our orders...
Looks like they've
found the ark after all.
[rustling]
[TENYO'S BROTHER] Y'know,
sis, it's not the best idea
to eat right before we work.
[KOZUKI] Only reason
I was helping these freaks
was so I could steal
the ark first chance I got.
Never thought I be neck deep
in all this other crap.
[sighs]
[MINAMI]
Please forgive me.
[PROFESSOR] It's fine...
You successfully
distracted the White Girl.
Our plans have been
fully realized...
But it's only bound
to get more dangerous.
I think you two should leave.
What about you?
I must remain here.
I'm expecting
someone to arrive.
[RINKA] Found you!
[grunts, gasps]
It's time the White Girl
and I face each other.
[RINKA] Hm!
[PROFESSOR]
Rinka Urushiba...
I'm impressed
with your tenacity.
And I do not impress easily.
[RINKA gasps]
Now... I'd suggest
killing the right one first.
[RINKA grunts]
[PROFESSOR] Did you forget that
we're at the top of a tower?
There's not exactly
any place for you to run.
[RINKA]
Now, Kuroi! Do it!
Huh?
[KUROI yells]
[gasps]
[RINKA] Kuroi, no!
Such a waste of your power...
What's the point
of invisibility
if I can see your bloodlust?
[PROFESSOR] You've put up a
remarkable fight, White Girl.
But this how it ends.
[RINKA] I can't give up now.
Not after I've come this far.
[RINKA] I'm so close...
So close to finding Kyotaro.
[RINKA] Is this
really it? It can't be.
[RINKA] Kyotaro... Please.
Kyotaro?!
[gasps]
[PELICO yells]
[PROFESSOR groans]
[PELICO]
Your deception is stunning...
But another telepath,
such as myself,
can easily neutralize it.
[KYOTARO] Uuh!
What?
I knew this would happen...
You refused
to stop fighting...
and pushed yourself
way past your limit...
I'm proud of you.
How providential...
Yet Again Destiny throws you
to your knees before me.
[grunts]
[KYOTARO breathes heavily]
Okay, Minami...
I'd like you
to kill Kyotaro now.
[gasps]
[PROFESSOR]
Go ahead, my child...
and before my eyes this time...
I'm certain that he's
incapable of shooting you.
That's messed up.
[MINAMI exhales]
[KYOTARO sighs lightly]
[KYOTARO quavered breathing]
--[MINAMI] Tell me why.
--[KYOTARO] What?
Why did you have to
choose her instead of me?
What're you saying?
[MINAMI quavered breathing]
Now I understand...
Thank you.
[MINAMI gasps]
I honestly didn't
realize that you still
cared for me so much.
And I'm very grateful for it.
[gasps]
[KYOTARO]
But if you wanna know...
it all goes back to
the day when you disappeared.
Losing you...
was like losing my family.
He made me!
[KYOTARO] It's not that
I felt... "abandoned."
I just felt powerless
not knowing where you were,
because... I couldn't
do anything for you.
Couldn't help you.
[MINAMI sighs]
But when Rinka came along,
she helped me find the strength
that I had deep down.
She barely knew me...
but that didn't stop her from
choosing to believe in me.
[KYOTARO]
That's all I needed.
And it was just as easy
for me to believe in her.
If things had been different...
If only you had believed--
[KYOTARO] If only I had
let myself believe in you.
Mm. But instead...
I was too worried
about protecting you.
[MINAMI gasps]
[KYOTARO gasps]
[MINAMI sobbing]
Now, Kozuki...
Grab both Minami and
the ark and get out of here.
[KOZUKI] Huh?
I've had a change of heart.
It's not the right time
to hand the ark over to them.
Them who?
[PROFESSOR]
Just do as I've asked.
[KOZUKI pants]
Minami!
I'm sorry, Kyotaro.
Kyotaro!
Hey! I'm just following
orders, dude, okay?
You've finally
got your chance.
I sincerely doubt you'll
find a better opportunity
to kill me than right now.
Same for you.
But you haven't yet.
Why the hell do you
always let me live?
You've had more than
your fair share
of chances to kill me!
[KYOTARO] Why did you
save me all those years ago?
Was it because you knew
that I would stop you someday?
[PROFESSOR] Of course not.
I saved you... because I
sensed a miracle in you.
[KYOTARO grunts]
Of all your trials...
this decision
will haunt you the most.
[clanking]
[KUROI] Heh!
[KYOTARO groans]
Uh!
You're really here.
[gasps]
--[PROFESSOR groans]
--[KYOTARO] Professor!
[PROFESSOR]
I had a feeling the prey
would find
the bait irresistible.
Kyotaro! You have to run!
I chose to take this path
of my own volition.
You need to live.
Become the hero you are.
Uhhh... Any idea
what the hell that thing is?
[KYOTARO, RINKA gasp]
[CROWD murmurs, chatter]
[CROWD screaming]
[YODANI] The city has
fallen into utter chaos...
And only seven days have passed
since they released the fish.
Crime has risen
to a staggering rate...
And virtually every offense
was perpetrated by an esper.
Do you think there's
any way it'll get better?
Or just worse?
I have no idea...
The only thing I know...
is we've gotta stay hidden
for the time being.
Honestly, I'd kind of
like to take a little break
from danger for
the next few months.
Look at this...
We put our necks
on the line for this city
and it still goes to shit
the first chance it gets.
It didn't matter.
We weren't able
to stop anything.
[RINKA] Enough moping.
The battle's far from over...
And yeah, I know,
it's gone to hell out there.
But...
we've been through hell...
So why let it stop us now?
You're right about that.
[RINKA]
We've done this before
and I know
we can do it again...
So how 'bout it?
I need you on my side, Kyotaro.
Only espers
can beat other espers.
And who does
that leave but us?
[gasps] Hm!
[KOZUKI] I worked really hard
to make that, y'know.
You've gotta eat someday.
Fine, just sit
there with your sword,
I'll celebrate
the New Year on my own.
Oh, shit!
This is live, folks!
They seem to have
no regard for our--aah!
Uh! There's a girl!
[KYOTARO]
Surrender, criminals!
You've invoked
the justice of Crow Head!
A new hero... for a new age!
[FEMALE REPORTER 1A]
They've come!
The vigilante espers known as...
Jeez, look at him...
Thinks he's a super hero...
Must be nice
to be that delusional.
A hero, huh? Hm.
Die, you costumed freak!
[MALE CULPRIT 12B] Huh?
--[RINKA yells]
--[MALE CULPRIT 12B groans]
[RINKA] I know there's not just
one definition of justice...
It means something
different to everyone.
I also know what it's like
to live with the fear
of retaliation,
and to collapse
beneath my own limits.
But... knowing these things...
[RINKA] They don't
change my feelings.
As long as I have
the person I love...
And as long as I can give some
kind of hope to the world...
[RINAK, MINAMI] There's a
reason for me to keep fighting!