[grunts]
[gasps]
Well, crap. You got skills.
And I'm not gonna go easy
on you just 'cuz you're a girl!
[RINKA]
Oh, man. He can really move.
[grunts]
[YODANI] I suggest treating
this like a real battle.
And by the way,
if you actually hit him.
I'll buy you a steak!
Seriously? Oh god!
Did you forget that
we're sparring?
Try to give me a
little respect here.
Y'know, I came all
the way down here.
You could at least attempt
to stay focused.
Ugh.
[AYUMU]
Is that your serious stance?
Bring it, White Girl!
[grunts]
Master Roshi's spoken
pretty highly of you.
[RINKA yelps]
He completely blocked her.
And the media sure seems
to think you're hot shit.
[RINKA]
Whoa! His reflexes are nuts!
But if this is the best
that you can do...
[RINKA]
Ow!
...and you plan to take
on those terrorists,
then you'll die.
[RINKA]
What's with him?
It's like he's dodging my
attacks before I make them.
It's sad that the idea
of steak is enough
to make you lose
your concentration!
[AYUMU] This training is
wasted on someone like you!
You're helpless!
Like a child!
Careful, Rinka!
[PEGGY squeaks]
[grunts]
[AYUMU] And you? You wanna
take a shot, little girl?
Think ya can last any
longer than she did?
Don't piss yourself.
I'm just screwin' with ya.
[MURASAKI sighs]
I wouldn't waste my time.
A sneeze would
probably kill you.
I'm heading home.
I've got some studying to do.
[PEGGY coos]
[RINKA]
It's so weird.
It's not like he's faster
than Master Roshi.
But he moves like he already
knows what I'm gonna do next.
Wait, a minute...
He caught it
without even looking!
[PEGGY]
Waah.
Just as I thought.
Don't attack unless
you're really gonna hit.
What just happened?
I'm confused.
He didn't try to deflect it.
He didn't even flinch
because he already knew
I wasn't actually gonna hit him.
Are you saying...?
[RINKA]
Yep. He's gotta be an esper.
He's just like us.
[MURASAKI]
What? Precognition?
But I've got a hunch
that he can't really see
all that far into the future.
Really? What gives
you that idea?
[RINKA] Because he wasn't
expecting us to ambush him
on his way home.
Seems like he would've
chosen a different path
to avoid us if he could
see that far ahead.
[MURASAKI]
Yeah. Good point.
[RINKA]
If I had to guess.
His vision of the future
is probably always active,
mixing with the present.
[MURASAKI]
So then,
how do you beat
someone like that?
[RINKA] No matter how much
he knows what's coming.
There's gotta be
some point where he just
can't avoid an attack.
In other words,
I have to overcome
his reaction speed.
Which means I have to perfect
the hundred fist punch!
[PEGGY, MURASAKI yelp]
[RINKA]
Hundred Fist Punch!
Uh. I don't think
that's a real thing.
Well, not yet.
[MURASAKI]
Sure.
[panting]
[AYUMU]
If that's enough to make you
lose your concentration,
then you're too helpless
to even bother with training.
[RINKA]
I am not helpless.
But, if I can't even beat him...
[RINKA] ...there's no way
I can beat Minami.
[YODANI] People's thoughts
can overwhelm them
when they hit a wall.
They become distressed
when they cannot
puzzle out an answer.
So how is one able to succeed
when their thoughts
are of no use to them?
And no clear answer exists?
You simply don't think.
You push right on
through the wall.
[YODANI] Hoh. The girl's
a quick learner, isn't she?
[YODANI] The secret of C.P.C.
lies in the counter offense.
No matter their speed,
your opponent's attack
will create an opening.
[YODANI]
Only attack once they attack.
Use their own force
and strength against them
in a grappling counter.
Repeat the move
thousands of times
until it's drilled
into your mind.
Train your body to
remember the timing
until you can
respond instinctively.
Repeat it over and over until
your body moves on its own
without thought.
Please, you know I love you.
Just stop. You can't
do this to me, Taro.
I'm a married woman.
[JIRO] That cretin
doesn't deserve the love
of a woman like you.
[HANAKO]
Stop.
So my ESP's
only contact based.
It's like I can't even feel it
unless I'm touching something.
[PEGGY coos]
[MURASAKI]
Get out of there, Peggy.
Rinka's bag is not a play pen.
[PEGGY]
Ooh?
That's weird, she left
her nightstick behind.
Hm...
How am I now just
coming up with the idea
to use my ESP on a weapon?
[MURASAKI yelps]
[HANAKO]
Taro, I'm sorry!
[REIA] Ayumu. How are your
studies coming along?
There's no better
time than summer
to blow past the other kids.
Yeah.
[REIA] Don't go easy
on yourself just because
you're in middle school.
You'll be applying for
colleges before you know it.
[AYUMU] What about you,
Mom, how've you been?
The election's right
around the corner.
[REIA]
I know.
That's why it's important that
I can sell the country my plan
to deal with these
awful terrorists.
We have to take our nation
back for our people.
My proposal is the only
way we can truly be safe.
I guess.
[REIA] Goodness, these
espers are such demons.
The world would be
better off without them.
[AYUMU] I've got other things
I could be doing, y'know.
Make a move already!
[AYUMU] What's with you?
Let's just get this over with.
I don't wanna catch a cold.
[AYUMU]
She's just standing there.
I guess she's decided to
abandon the offensive strategy.
And this is bound to be
a different fight
now that she knows
about my powers.
Last time she had assumed
it was a normal sparring match.
No matter how many
outcomes I can see.
Her power keeps
screwing up the variables.
[AYUMU]
On top of that.
She's got a counter move
prepared for every attack
I can think of.
[AYUMU] But we're just gonna
stand here all day at this rate.
[AYUMU yells]
[AYUMU]
As long as I know it's coming,
I can still counter her counter!
[RINKA yells]
[AYUMU grunts]
[AYUMU] If I can see it,
then I can stop it!
[AYUMU]
A kick won't work!
[YODANI] He can think ahead
as many moves as he wants.
But his body simply can't keep
up with all of the possible
future permutations
that he sees.
[AYUMU yells]
[YODANI] The quicker he thinks,
the slower he gets.
[AYUMU]
Ow, shit!
[YODANI] Rinka is responding
instinctively to his attacks.
Even if he could see
a thousand moves ahead,
she'd counter all of them.
[RINKA]
C.P.C. Secret Technique!
[AYUMU groans]
[RINKA]
Thousand Hand Counter!
[YODANI]
He's had enough!
Man. I knew I shouldn't
have attacked first.
[YODANI] I'm impressed
with how far you've come
in such a short time, Rinka.
[RINKA] Thank you for your
guidance, Master Roshi.
[YODANI]
It wasn't just me.
You had many of the necessary
skills from the years
your father spent training you.
You're right.
[YODANI]
As for you.
Your body just can't
keep up with your mind.
Don't give me that crap!
That was a fluke.
I just had my
guard down, that's all!
I'll kick her ass next time.
There's no way I'm gonna
lose to a girl more than once.
[MURASAKI]
You really think so?
Let's test it out.
Unless you're too scared.
Is that why you
haven't fought me?
Well, this seems
out of character.
Fair warning though.
Keep your guard up
so you don't get hurt.
Y'see, my dad's a
kung-fu movie fanatic
and he bought these
nunchucks at an auction.
You wanna guess who owned them?
[AYUMU]
You're joking, right?
The weapon can't win
the fight for you--
[MURASAKI] Hwaaa! Ha!
[AYUMU yells]
[YODANI] Her body's much
faster than his mind!
[MURASAKI]
Dragon Remember!
What the hell was that?
[RINKA, YODANI]
It was a miracle!
[PEGGY]
Uwaah?
[KYOTARO groans]
[panting]
[MINAMI]
It's pointless.
He already told you.
He overwrote the
destination in your mind.
All you're doing
is wearing yourself out.
You're not going
to escape this room.
You're still going
through with this?
It's terrorism.
Of course. Why would we stop?
We've only just started.
Everything we've
worked so hard for
has finally begun.
Minami...
[KYOTARO]
It's sad.
I wish you could see
things differently.
If only you had someone
who could've saved you
from all of this.
[KYOTARO]
The same way that I was saved.
Then maybe you could
see that justice
doesn't come from hatred.
[KYOTARO]
Uh--
Terrorism.
Do you know where
the word comes from?
[KYOTARO]
Huh?
[MINAMI] It was first
coined in France.
It's the use of fear
as a political tool.
You and I are no strangers
to that kind of fear.
My parents and your mom.
They all died for
someone else's political gain.
[MINAMI] There are times
I almost trick myself
into thinking that none
of it really happened.
It's like I turn my mind off
and float through
every normal boring day.
It's strange.
It almost feels like I'm
outside the flow of time.
[KYOTARO] You may not feel
the passage of time, but...
But it's still affecting you.
I can see you
changing with every day.
[MINAMI]
How have I changed?
Huh? Well it's hard to explain.
But you just seem more mature.
Even though we're the same age,
I can't help but feel like
I'm getting left behind.
[KYOTARO]
Minami.
I refuse to change
the way that you have.
If growing up means
becoming like you,
I'd rather stay a kid.
[REIA]
These espers are a plague.
They will destroy every last
vestige of our society,
unless we can
put a stop to them.
We need to round up every
last one of these monsters,
research them and protect
our peaceful way of life.
We must band together
to defeat this menace.
And stand with our
hearts as one.
Let's make them regret
their acts of terrorism.
[AYUMU] I doubt her
campaign would go so hot
if people knew her kid
was an esper.
I know she'd
certainly be shocked.
[MURASAKI]
Oh. Hey, Ayumu.
Nunchucks girl!
What the heck're you
doing down here?
I'm just heading over
to my dad's house.
I'm actually gonna
take these back to him.
But you can't fight without
those things, right?
Are you giving up the hero game?
Of course not.
But moving like a master at this
level is just too hard on me.
I can't really keep it up for
much more than twenty seconds.
It basically feels like
I'm kicking my own butt.
My whole body aches
like a truck hit me.
So y'know. I figured
I'll take a look
and see what other
weapons my dad has.
I'll borrow something that's
a little more my speed.
[AYUMU] Sounds like you
get along pretty well
with your family.
Huh? What was that?
Forget it, it was nothing.
But lemme ask you this.
You're still just a kid,
so why do you feel the
need to fight so badly?
What's my reason?
I don't have one in particular.
[AYUMU]
What?
I fight 'cuz it's
the right thing to do.
[AYUMU]
Oh, man, you're so naïve.
We can fight for
justice all we want.
But that doesn't mean this
world's ever gonna accept us.
[BOTH gasp]
[SAKAMOTO grunts]
[AYUMU]
An explosion? Wait.
This is a premonition.
There's still time!
[MURASAKI] Uh...
[AYUMU gasps]
Get down, right now!
[MURASAKI]
What?
[SAKAMOTO]
This is Divine Retribution!
[AYUMU yells]
[AYUMU] Oh, crap.
Of course he's an esper.
[AYUMU gasps]
My god. They're all dead!
Stand up, bigot.
Don't fight. You did
this to yourself.
[AYUMU gasps]
You are nothing more
than a parasite
that feeds on the
weak and the uneducated.
Politicians like you have filled
this world with suffering.
[screams]
Mom!
Well here's your chance
to suffer for a change.
No. Leave her alone!
My leg! I twisted it!
Why'd this have to happen now?
Agh!
[gasps]
Are you crazy?
That guy'll kill you!
That freakin' hurt.
Which one of you swine
threw that at me?
[AYUMU] What'd I tell you?
He's gonna murder us!
Get away from that
woman right now!
What?
Step back or I'll
throw another one.
Oh, yeah?
So you actually
admit you threw it.
Little bitch.
If you think I won't kill
you just 'cuz you're a kid,
you're dead wrong!
[gasps]
[AYUMU]
Murasaki!
Wait! That didn't just happen.
It's the future.
[MURASAKI] Get away from
that woman right now!
Step back or I'll
throw another one.
Oh, yeah?
So you actually
admit you threw it.
Wait, no, please,
just wait a second!
Please, we're really sorry!
She shouldn't have done it!
It was wrong, and I swear,
we're so sorry!
Please forgive us!
[MURASAKI]
What're you doing?
[SAKAMOTO]
Heh.
[AYUMU]
I promise, I won't let her do
anything that stupid again!
Say you're sorry!
This guy shoots electricity
out of his hands.
You're gonna be instantly
cremated if he hits you.
Yeah, but, he's about
to kill that woman.
[gasps]
[groans]
[screams]
[AYUMU screams] Does every
possible future suck?!
[AYUMU]
Excuse me, sir!
I don't think you
wanna do that.
[SAKAMOTO]
Why the hell not?
Listen. Kid.
The last thing you wanna do
is try to play hero with me.
Uh...
[AYUMU]
Don't do it!
[MURASAKI]
But...
[SAKAMOTO] I don't trust all
this whispering you're doing.
Say goodbye to your afro.
And the rest of your head.
[AYUMU]
I do not have an afro.
Just calm down, alright?
You don't wanna kill
a fellow esper, do you?
You're an esper?
[AYUMU]
I don't have a choice.
I gotta stop him somehow.
My only chance is to
deflect the electricity
with my belt buckle.
But...
[AYUMU grunts]
[AYUMU] Every future
scenario has me missing
and dying if I try that.
[AYUMU] What do I do?
Think of something.
Everyone's gonna die if I don't.
One small thing can
change everything.
But what? Think!
So you're telling me
you're a chosen one?
You better not be
lying to me, kid.
[AYUMU]
Something. Anything, dammit!
Something that can
alter the future!
[AYUMU]
The water pipe! That's it!
Wha--?
[AYUMU grunts]
You little son of a bitch!
[AYUMU]
Damnit! He didn't fall in!
[SAKAMOTO growls]
[AYUMU]
No way. I won't make it!
[MURASAKI]
Wa-cha! Hiyyya!
Whoa!
[AYUMU]
Well, crap. I still got shocked.
[MURASAKI] Me, too. I don't
think I can move my body.
Do you wanna die
before you finish
elementary school?
That was really
freaking reckless.
It had to be done.
And a hero's gotta do
what a hero's gotta do.
Right!
[BOTH giggle]
[REIA]
Ayumu?
You're okay! I'm so glad
you're safe, Mom!
[REIA]
I need to know.
Are you really one of them?
Please don't tell me
you're an esper.
[PEGGY] Scene 08, "Fruition,
Girls Set into Motion."