Uh!
Why, so you can
cry over her corpse?
[grunts]
No, that's not true.
That's impossible!
[KYOTARO grunts]
[groans]
[KYOTARO] Damnit.
That's all I've got.
[KYOTARO] Please, Rinka.
Just stay alive. For me.
[explosion]
[police sirens]
[MALE ANNOUNCER 1A]
It's been ten days since
the ESP restrictions
were put in place.
Many terrorist attacks
have been directed at
esper detainment forces
in that time.
Chaos reigns in the city.
Huh?
'Scuse me there, ma'am.
Whoa, hey!
You're the White Girl!
I hate to say so,
but you gotta scram.
Trouble follows you, and I don't
think I wanna get shot today.
[OLD MAN] Mm!
I'm so happy you can
actually see them too.
Wow. Can you
believe this, Rinka?
I miss you.
[RINKA] They beat me down,
but I fought back.
But now I'm not even sure why.
Espers have a duty.
It's our job to protect people.
[RINKA]
I believed it was our duty.
That we had to be the ones
to stop the Professor.
But then...
[RINKA] Did I really
protect anyone?
And will I even be able
to help without my powers?
I know I'm not
cut out to be a hero.
Because everything
I had is gone.
You promised you'd never
leave me behind,
but now I'm alone and
it's hopeless without you.
Please come back to me.
I need you.
[KYOTARO] I knew you were my
hero from the first time we met.
[gasps]
Kyotaro?
There's no point anymore.
I'll never be a hero.
[gasps]
[RINKA] There's just
no point without you.
Uh!
Rinka!
[coughing]
I'm back. But I was dead?
[MINAMI]
You were this close to it.
Your power's not
strong enough, okay?
You can't get to
Tokyo on your own.
Uh!
If I was supposed to die,
I don't understand
why you've saved me twice now.
That's what my father wanted.
But I had to trust my feelings.
[gasps] So you have
feelings when it's me?
Did you feel anything for all
the other people you killed?
[MINAMI] I'm not
some heartless monster.
You would never accuse me
of that, if you really knew.
[KYOTARO]
What do you mean? Knew what?
The truth, Kyotaro.
My mother and
your parents didn't die
the way you were told.
[beeping]
[RINKA] Mm!
[TORADA] We've implanted a
wiretap and GPS in your arm.
The White Girl
won't be escaping our
detainment center
anytime soon.
Fuckin' pigs.
Hey, check it out.
[SORIMACHI] Hm?
All these prisoners
are espers.
How can they get away with this?
[YODANI] By calling it
a detainment center
instead of a jail.
Despite the prison aesthetic,
it's surprisingly comfortable.
[RINKA]
They got you, too?
[YODANI] Yeah, I couldn't run
after they tranked me.
So I'm stuck in this chair
for the time being.
Will your legs be okay?
[YODANI]
It's of no concern.
I'm simply relieved to see
you're alive and in one piece.
[gasps] Wait, where's my dad?
Please tell me he's okay.
[YODANI sighs]
What? An isolation capsule?
[YODANI] We all get
to sit around up here,
feeling sorry for ourselves,
but those with powers
like teleportation,
fire, and electricity
can't be controlled so well.
They're all locked up
and under forced sedation.
[RINKA]
Uh... That's horrible.
[YODANI] I'm ashamed.
I was helpless to defend him.
[squaks]
Watch your fingers there.
He can remove your powers
if you get too close to him.
Oh. If he's that dangerous,
why don't you just lemme
go ahead and
kill him to be safe?
Uh-uuh!
That's thoughtful of you,
but I would have
killed him already
if it didn't mean
releasing the fish
he's captured.
It could be very bad if
those fish found new hosts.
Much less is risked by
keeping him prisoner.
[KOZUKI] Heh.
So the little guy's in
his forever home, huh?
[sighs]
[KOZUKI] And this big gold box
over here is supposed to be
the source of our powers?
[KOZUKI] It looks like a replica
prop from a movie I saw
about the uh,
the Ark of the Covenant.
Astute observation, Kozuki.
But I can assure you
it's not a replica.
[KOZUKI] Huh?
[PROFESSOR] Many people
assume the Ark is just a myth,
but we've experienced
the miracle of its existence.
[KYOTARO]
What are you saying?
Both our families were caught
in soldiers' crossfire!
They were victims of
some goddamn civil war!
Sure, that's the
official version.
But no one's ever
told you the truth.
[distant gun shots]
[gasps]
[YOUNG KYOTARO] But. Both of
you guys are going this time?
Yeah, the dig
needs us both, kiddo,
and it could take a while.
We'll be back
before you can miss us.
And you know,
this discovery is
going to be tremendous.
We'll probably be
famous after this!
It's that cool?
[JUTARO]
It's super cool!
[BOTH laugh]
[YOUNG KYOTARO] Dad! Mom!
[gasping, sobbing]
[dark piano tune plays]
[GENERAL] Ooh...!
You really did it!
We are looking at the
true Ark of the Covenant!
Yes. But, General,
there's more to learn,
like who brought it
here and how they...
[GENERAL]
You and your research!
It's obvious God brought this
here for us to find!
You've read the Old Testament.
This is none other than the
legendary weapon of gospel
that brought down
the walls of Jericho!
The Ark! The box of
the Ten Commandments!
No, wait!
[GENERAL gasps] My god!
The actual stone tablets.
Finally.
At long last, they're mine!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[GENERAL] Uh! Uuuh...!
[PROFESSOR]
What the hell have you done?
What's happening?
Is this even real?
[gasps]
[SAIRA]
Honey, can you hear me?
[PROFESSOR gasps]
Darling. Are you hurt?
Mm. No, I'm all right.
What happened?
[JUTARO] Uh! General
Pompous Ass screwed our dig.
That idiot just shattered
five out of
the Ten Commandments.
[PROFESSOR] Shit.
But, what came out of it?
It looked like flying,
glowing goldfish.
Then they swam through us.
Say what?
Wait. Are you saying that
you didn't see the fish?
They're the only reason
we lost consciousness
in the first place.
Uh, sure, guys.
I figured you passed out
from the shock of seeing
that moron breaking the tablet.
[laughs]
[KYOKA groans]
Hey, welcome back sweetie!
How you feeling?
Uh, fine, I guess,
but you're being a little loud.
What? Oh!
Sorry, sorry, babe!
Just stop it!
Your voice is too loud!
You're supposed to
shut up in a hospital!
Uh--holy shit you're on fire!
[KYOKA] Help me!
[SAIRA]
Get some water! Hurry!
--[JUTARO] From where?
--[SAIRA] Just hurry up!
[roars]
So you just imagine.
And it becomes a real thing?
That's pretty
un-frickin'-believable, man.
Yeah.
[JUTARO] Here, kitty.
--[JUTARO] Ow!
--[PROFESSOR] Oh! I'm sorry!
[JUTARO] Uh--
Interesting.
You can experience
the illusion touching
you physically.
But it can't
leave an actual mark.
[PROFESSOR] As I suspected,
those fish have somehow
changed our bodies
fundamentally.
It seemed like
a hallucination,
but if not, then what
principle animates it?
Are we different forever?
Look at you. You're gonna
get more wrinkles.
One worry at a time!
Sure.
[SAIRA chuckles]
This is simply astonishing,
Professor Azuma!
[PROFESSOR] General.
Your report
reads like a dream!
I can hardly
believe it, Professor!
So. I need to know
how to obtain these powers,
so I can be
a part of this dream!
It remains unclear.
I recommend we convene
a neutral panel
of international scientists.
[GENERAL]
No, we can't have that.
This research will be
exclusively contained here.
--[KYOKA, SAIRA, JUTARO gasp]
--[PROFESSOR] What?
The Ark will not
be leaving my country.
And I will have that power.
Until I do, none of you
will be permitted to leave.
[WASHIBANA] I'm sure the general
will be happy to reconsider.
[GENERAL]
Explain this. Who are you?
[PROFESSOR] I had a feeling
you might do this.
So I called an attaché
from Japan to represent us.
What?
Hello there. I'm from the
Department of Foreign Affairs.
My name's Washibana.
These negotiations
will continue through me.
Sound good?
[grunts] Ugh!
[PROFESSOR]
Don't be naïve.
It's impossible to think the
General's mind can be changed.
Involving the diplomat
may have damned us.
I think we're in real danger.
And all of you should prepare
to leave for Japan, right away.
[ALL gasp]
Don't you realize we'll
lose the ark if we leave?
Yes, but... I must
consider your lives as well.
Mm.
Hang on. You're staying?
[PROFESSOR] Only briefly. We'll
finish things here quickly.
I won't be the
General's lab rat.
Course not. Hey!
Come over for lunch tomorrow,
before we go on home.
You've really
gotta meet our son
before we all
high tail it to Japan!
Kyotaro's just amazing!
And he said that he wants to be
just like us when he grows up.
That's great!
--[cell phone rings]
--[PROFESSOR] Oh, sorry.
Yes? Hello?
Oh. Yes, Washibana.
[PROFESSOR] Please explain
the meaning of this.
Why have you brought us
here at this hour?
[WASHIBANA] Understand, I am
working on sending you home.
However, the General
has made certain
reasonable points
about the Ark.
[grunts] But he's late.
The big guy shoulda
been here already.
Let me just go check.
[PROFESSOR gasps]
[ALL gasp, yell]
--[gun fire]
--[ALL scream]
[rustling]
Wh-What happened?
[PROFESSOR] Jutaro. Kyoka.
Ah...
--[SAIRA groans]
--[PROFESSOR gasps]
[PROFESSOR] Saira!
[WASHIBANA]
As negotiated,
Japan will receive
one stone tablet.
The other, as well as
the ark, may remain with you.
Obviously, this "exchange"
must be kept confidential
in order to maintain diplomacy.
[GENERAL] Of course, sir.
Uh!
[WASHIBANA]
Oh, dear. How unfortunate.
[PROFESSOR]
What the hell have you done?
You were never here to help us.
My god. Did Japan order this?
What difference
could that possibly make?
Your fate is sealed, and there's
nothing you can do about it.
[PROFESSOR grunts]
[clinking]
[PROFESSOR gasps]
[birds chirping]
[YOUNG MINAMI] Uh. Uh?
Is that Daddy?
[gasps]
[PROFESSOR] In the end,
only I escaped the treacherous
dealings of
those two countries.
But, the repercussions
would reverberate
through my whole life.
[HEADMASTER]
It's fortunate you escaped.
However, you ignored
the warning to evacuate
and your research
fellows weren't so lucky.
Which means
the university cannot--
You're not understanding!
Evacuation warning?
None of that is remotely true.
The damn diplomat
sold my team out
to that piece of shit General!
[MALE 10A] The Professor wants
to blame the government
instead of facing the truth.
[FEMALE 10A] He should try
and take responsibility
like a real man.
[MALE 10B] Dude knows
the blame's on him.
[MALE 10C]
My guess is he's a nut job.
[PROFESSOR]
No one believed me.
My words fell on the deaf ears
of skeptics and worse.
[gasps]
The Japanese attaché!
He should know everything!
[PROFESSOR]
So I searched everywhere.
I was a desperate man.
[intense music plays]
[gasps]
--[PROFESSOR] Hm.
--[WASHIBANA] Uh!
[WASHIBANA groans]
[PROFESSOR inhales deeply]
[yells]
--[PROFESSOR inhales deeply]
--[squelch]
--[FEMALE 10B screams]
[CROWD murmurs, screams]
[PROFESSOR] Ultimately,
he was expendable, too.
And the truth was
lost with his life.
[PROFESSOR sobs]
Why did it have to--?
Why did it happen? Why?
The world is sick!
Full of disease!
I will cure it!
[roaring]
[distant screaming]
[growls]
How? Is it a demon?
[squelch]
[yells]
Uh! Professor!
[screams]
[GENERAL] W-Wait!
It was Washibana! He did it!
He planned the massacre
of your people!
Washibana's off the board.
[GENERAL gasps]
[PROFESSOR] Someone more
influential than you
has already tied up
that loose end.
There are plans
we know nothing about.
Some puppet master
pulling strings.
So I'll use the remaining
tablet to draw him out,
then I'll kill him slowly.
Painfully. Along with
his entire family.
[gun shot]
[grunts, groans]
No, Kyotaro!
[gun shot]
You little... bastard!
Dumb fucking kids! Aah!
[YOUNG KYOTARO] Uh...
[KYOKA]
"Kyotaro's just amazing!"
[mellow piano tune plays]
[PROFESSOR whimpers]
[inhales deeply]
[gasps]
[SAIRA groans]
What? No, stop it.
[SAIRA breathes heavily]
[gasping]
No, baby! Oh, God!
Please stay with me!
Don't worry. I love you.
[PROFESSOR sobbing]
[continues sobbing]
[screams]
[PROFESSOR] Soon enough.
This insane world will
come to the end it deserves.
Soon.
[MINAMI] They were murdered.
My mother, your parents.
They were taken from us.
You want revenge.
But what would that even do?
Our families are gone
and there's no way
that we can
ever bring them back!
[MINAMI]
I'm well aware of that.
[KYOTARO] Uh...
But can you honestly
tell me you're going to
forgive the people
who murdered your parents?
I--no, I can't.
Take a good look
deep inside yourself.
Can you really stand there
and tell me revenge is wrong?
Damnit!
What would Rinka do?
She'd follow her heart. But how?
[RINKA] Y'know,
people like those douchebags
really piss me off.
Uh--
They were
the douchebags, right?
Uh-huh.
Well that's a relief!
[KYOTARO chuckles]
Can't argue with that!
[KYOTARO moans]
We can't let the douchebags
control the world.
There's no way. And Rinka would
give her life to stop them.
For sure. Right?
[PEGGY] Whoa!
Scene 11, "Tokyo Girls War."