I know I should have told you.
But I only wanted to
protect you, that's all.
Listen, I promise you, Mom,
I'm not with the terrorists.
I'm still your son.
Just because I've
got these powers
doesn't mean I've changed.
[REIA]
No. No. Don't you get it?
It's not you I'm worried about!
I'm worried what it will do
to my election chances.
If my constituents find out,
the whole thing's over for me.
I won't just have to resign,
I'll also look like a fool
and the representatives
meet next week.
But, Mom, I wouldn't have
been able to save you.
If I didn't have these powers,
that guy would've killed you!
[gasps]
[AYUMU] Should I have just
let my mother die instead?
[RINKA, RINDOU grunting]
After a terrorist attack during
a local politician's speech,
the government has moved
defense forces into action
to protect the city
against the growing
esper threat.
It remains to be seen whether
the forces will have any effect.
[YODANI]
A very unsettling development.
Master, do you really think
that Ayumu is all right?
[RINDOU, RINKA]
Huh?
[YODANI]
He's safe for now.
Locked away at home,
deep in study.
Oh, okay.
[YODANI]
In the midst of personal strife,
he still wears a brave face.
[RINDOU] Master Roshi,
sorry to bail on ya,
but I gotta get to my job.
[YODANI]
Yes, fine.
[RINKA] Well, I guess
I'll run for a while.
[YODANI] Good. It's best
to keep yourself occupied
while you have no sparring
partner to do it for you.
[HOUSEWIFE 8A] Espers?
You mean like the ESP freaks?
The terrorists?
Y'can't even tell
who might be one.
I heard my cousin's girlfriend's
uncle is an esper.
[gasps]
[MALE 8A] Sign our petition
against the espers!
Please help us in our fight!
[CROWD]
Stand up and fight!
[MALE 8B] What they've
done is unforgivable!
[CROWD]
We won't forgive them!
[MALE 8A]
We need your help!
Please sign our petition
against the espers!
Let's take our city back!
[ASHITABA]
Hey, look! Rinka!
[GIRLS giggling]
[HARUMOA] Long time,
stranger, what are you up to?
Oh, I uh...
I'm just out for a jog.
[RUU]
Really? In this crazy heat?
Yeah.
[ASHITABA] Betcha can't
guess where we're going.
We got passes to
Bunny Wonder Park!
[RUU, HARUMOA]
Hey!
[RUU] So what have you
been up to this summer?
Me?
Like been on any hot
dates with that senior?
Dude's hot!
[RUU, ASHITABA]
Mm-hm!
[ASHITABA] Oh, or, did you
guys already break up?
[RUU]
Aw! That sucks!
[RINKA]
Sorry, I've gotta finish my run.
I will be taking Kyotaro back.
No way!
[MOTHER 6A]
Please don't leave.
Rescue my child.
[RINKA]
Drop him!
[MINAMI]
You'll have to take him from me.
But you will fail. And in
the meantime, they'll die.
[MOTHER 6A]
Please! I'm begging you!
The amusement park.
[RINKA] I want you to
promise me something then,
hero to hero.
I need you to swear
to me that next time,
no matter what happens, you
won't disappear on me again.
Cross my heart.
All right!
To celebrate the birth
of our new superhero,
I'll take you to
the amusement park!
[RINKA]
What? No, don't worry about it!
[gasps]
Kyotaro, I wish you were here.
So we could see
this view together.
[gasps]
[KOBATO giggles]
[RINKA shrieks]
All by your lonesome at
the amusement park, huh?
Your life must really suck.
Your power is just
like mine. That's crazy.
I'll do you a favor
and end your loneliness.
[gasps]
[CROWD screaming]
[KOBATO cackles]
[KOBATO]
Yes!
I've finally got a
murder under my belt
and that's just the start!
I'm one of them now.
An actual ESP terrorist!
[RINKA]
You freaking idiot!
You're celebrating way too soon!
[KOBATO]
Aw, you bitch! Let's try again.
[gasps]
[gasps] Stop it!
[growls]
Die!
Huh?
[grunting]
[RINKA]
These powers are a gift.
We can do amazing
things with them!
I'm not gonna let you
use them to kill people!
[MINAMI]
Of course she'd be here.
We need to do something
about our "hero."
[NABESHIMA]
I'll take her in,
but I've gotta
be sure it's safe.
I mean, are you
absolutely certain
her powers aren't
gonna come back?
[PEGGY]
Woo!
Fuckin' duck!
[PEGGY squeals]
[MURASAKI]
There, there.
Dammit.
If I could'a just
killed a few people,
I would've gotten to meet him.
[RINKA]
Him, who?
[YODANI] Why don't ya tell us
who you're talking about,
little girl?
[KOBATO]
Who do ya think?
The living god
of the new mankind.
[NABESHIMA]
Who the hell is that?
[YODANI]
You mean the Professor?
[KOBATO] Yeah, it's not like
I know him or anything,
but his agent came to test
my ESP powers personally.
[KOBATO]
If you wanna join their group,
you have to show her that you
can kill using your powers.
That's sick.
Roshi.
[YODANI] He's singling out
the most fanatical candidates
with a kill test.
[KOBATO]
That's right!
The test is how many people
can you kill, kill, kill!
[KOBATO cackling]
[MALE YOUTH GUIDANCE 8A]
You trying to look like
that esper with your hair?
Answer my question!
[AMIE]
It's natural.
I don't believe it!
You're out here pretty late
for a school night.
Where do you go to school?
Nowhere.
[MALE YOUTH GUIDANCE 8A]
What?
School annoyed me
too much. So I quit.
[MALE YOUTH GUIDANCE 8A]
What about work?
You've got a job, right?
[AMIE]
Work annoys me, too. So I don't.
[MALE YOUTH GUIDANCE 8B]
How do you expect
to have a future
with that attitude?
You can still get
your life together.
You can go back to school,
and get a job
and grow up to
have a happy life.
[AMIE sighs]
I just wanna kill everyone.
[MALE YOUTH GUIDANCE 8A]
Alright, kid.
You need to listen when I--
[MINAMI]
You should take our test.
[AMIE]
What?
It's the only way
you'll ever be free.
[MALE SHOP KEEPER 8A]
I'm so sorry!
Please accept my apology!
[SALARYMAN 8A] You've lost
our business for good!
[MALE SHOP KEEPER 8A]
Rin, you dumb slut.
If you punch a customer
one more time,
then I'm gonna have to beat
the ever-living shit out of you.
I'm totally super sorry!
That's the last time.
I swear I won't do it again!
Can you please unhook
these chains now, mister?
[MALE SHOP KEEPER 8A]
Nice try.
I don't believe a
damn word you say.
Oh, then you do have a brain.
Listen close.
I pay damn good money
to your parents.
So I can make good use of you!
Now don't cause me
any more trouble!
My V-card's not getting punched.
There's no way in hell
that's gonna happen.
Not in this shithole.
And what do you think your
maidenhead is worth, slut?
Don't make me laugh!
If that's what you want,
then I can make my money
by chopping you up
and selling you in pieces!
But, I'm a nice guy, Rin.
So you get to keep your life and
make money for me in other ways.
Your existence is as meaningless
as the lives of those
ants over there.
I can crush you whenever I want.
[RIN]
Scumbag.
What now? The fuck you say?
I hope you die. Painfully!
What did you say, bitch?
Take our test.
[MINAMI]
It'll be worth it.
[FEMALE REPORTER 1A]
Inside parliament,
debate is raging over
the new ESP law.
Guards are stationed
around the building
amid fear of more
terrorist attacks.
These espers possess a
range of tremendous powers.
There's no certainty the
police can withstand them.
Ideally, we would have help
from our own team of espers.
[FEMALE REPORTER 1A]
We wonder what the White Girl
will do, Despite her
previous actions,
there's no certainty
she'll come to our aid.
All we can really do
is hope and wait.
The White Girl
and her associates
have assisted since the
first attack on Tokyo tower,
rescuing victims and
fighting esper terrorists,
Let's hope government officials
have the good sense
to trust these heroes.
Ha. Heroes, eh?
The White Girl
is a bud of hope.
And something must be done
about her before she blossoms.
Now is the time to
reveal her weakness.
[gasps]
[PROFESSOR]
Are you prepared, Minami?
Ha! Damn, Kozuki,
you've got some
freakin' awesome tricks, girl.
[KOZUKI] Well, it's pretty
convenient, I guess.
But things being too easy all
the time is like totally boring.
I need to find something extra
special to get myself worked up.
First world problems, huh?
[KOZUKI] I'm not bitching, I get
loads of fun out of it too.
So, what does
your superpower do?
[RIN]
Oh, me? It's a surprise!
Kay... Well, what's your
story over there?
Don't ask such boring questions.
[KOZUKI]
Okay, so, like,
don't you know it's
rude not to look at
the person speaking to you?
[AMIE]
You're better off.
Oh yeah? What the
hell's that mean?
[crash]
[panting]
[MINAMI] Can you tell me what
Kyotaro is doing right now?
[SUKESABURO] It seems he's
given up on trying to escape
for the time being.
[MINAMI]
Finally.
What crawled up her butt?
[KAKUNOSHIN]
She has many burdens.
More than one person
should carry.
[KOZUKI] That's a little vague,
what kind of burdens?
[KAKUNOSHIN]
The weight of the entire world.
[MINAMI gasps]
[KYOTARO]
Just as I thought!
The Professor's barrier
may work on me,
but I can still teleport if I
grab someone who's not affected!
How long is it gonna
take you to learn?
Huh?
You should know by now
that there's no point
in trying to escape.
[KYOTARO]
Okay, I get it.
But I'm not just trying
to escape, you know,
I'm trying to hold on to
a little bit of hope.
I don't understand.
Why don't you want
us to succeed?
[KYOTARO] Because,
no one should be allowed
to control others.
And you just can't
wipe people out.
Why the hell shouldn't we?
They're killing
themselves anyway.
They're more likely to survive
under my father's rule.
That's bullshit,
and you know it.
There's so much more
that humans can do.
That's the bullshit.
[KYOTARO] I wish you could
tell me what happened to you.
Why have you changed so much?
And why have you
stayed the same?
I thought you would understand
because humans have
hurt your family
just as much as
they have hurt mine.
You should hate them too.
But I don't.
[MINAMI]
Humans aren't worth it.
So you believe they have
potential and should be saved.
But that doesn't
mean you're right.
It means you're a naïve child.
[KYOTARO]
Fine, that may be true.
But it still doesn't
change the way I feel.
[KYOTARO]
The people I know?
They showed me
the good in humanity.
[MINAMI]
I give up.
Go back to your people.
[KYOTARO]
What? Seriously?
[MINAMI]
I can't convince you.
Your mind is clearly made up
You mean it?
Why would I lie?
Go run back to your
precious Rinka.
I'm finally starting to feel
like my bad-ass self again.
[PEGGY]
Waah!
[MURASAKI]
You'll be fighting in no time!
I hope so. Hey?
Whatcha doin'?
You've been sweatin'
in the kitchen all day.
[MURASAKI] It's just a
little friendly present.
[KUROI]
For who?
[MURASAKI]
What do you mean?
It's for one of
our friends, naturally!
--For a guy? Are you
--Hey, Let go of me!
fallin' in love? Who is he?
Are you, like, totally in love?
[MURASAKI]
Leave me alone!
You're crazy!
That's not it at all!
[KUROI]
Oh, I'm so sure!
How am I gonna face
the other representatives?
I appreciate you saving my life.
I'm truly grateful that you did,
but do I deserve to
have an esper son?
This chose me.
Nobody ever asked me if I
wanted to be some weird esper.
[tapping]
[AYUMU yelps]
[AYUMU]
A flying penguin?!
Wait. I know you.
Weren't you with Master Roshi?
[PEGGY squeaking]
Did you bring me something?
[PEGGY]
Ooh!
[AYUMU gasps]
[MURASAKI]
Dear Ayumu, I went back to where
we were attacked and
snooped around for a bit
until I found your glasses!
They were only a little
worse for wear!
[AYUMU]
Seriously?
What if she'd been
caught poking around?
[MURASAKI] Also, I made
some sweet cookies for you.
I really hope you like them!
P.S. Ayumu, I owe you my life
because you were
so cool that day.
You were like a total superhero,
and I swear to you that
I'll never forget it!
[AYUMU]
Wait, she thinks I was cool?
Please, we're really sorry!
She shouldn't have done it!
[AYUMU]
Nope.
Not cool, but she can
think whatever she wants.
[RINKA]
See ya later, everybody!
[RINDOU]
Have an awesome first day!
[RINKA] Going back to
school seems so normal.
[RINKA] I guess that's just
because everything else
is so bizarre.
[RINKA]
And still, no sign of Kyotaro.
[PEGGY]
Ahh!
[RINKA gasps]
Oh my god, you're back!
It's really you!
How in the heck
did you get away?
What about all your injuries?
I'm fine. They
weren't even real.
Tell me everything, please!
So, like...
They just all of a sudden
let you walk away?
Yeah.
It's like they just decided this
morning that I wasn't worth it.
I guess.
Now you're free,
but are you safe?
Well, Minami made it very clear
that I should stay out
of her way from now on.
It's like I never really
knew her at all.
I'm sorry.
But, I was so worried,
really everyone was so worried!
Why didn't you call us
the second you were freed?
[KYOTARO]
Because, when they let me go,
I just wanted to see you
as soon as possible.
[RINKA]
Huh?
[PEGGY]
Ah?
[RINKA]
Oh my god! Are you serious?
[piano playing]
[PROFESSOR] These myopic
children, consumed with
the distraction of love
and the hope it brings.
[PROFESSOR]
They can't even see the truth.
That nothing can
prevent their world
from coming to its death.
[PEGGY] Scene 09,
"Attack! ESP Girls."