[NABESHIMA] No name, no date
of birth, no fingerprints.
So we can't check for priors.
And not a single one
of the security cameras
caught jack. Hell, we can't even
establish probable cause.
Declarations from some whack-job
in a bird-head mask aren't
enough to hold her on.
So for now, we gotta assume
Black Fist is still at large.
[gasps]
[NABESHIMA grunts]
[FEMALE OFFICER 2A groans]
[MALE OFFICER 3A groans]
I'mma kick that girl's ass.
Bitch needs to mind
her own damn business.
Snow White is so fuckin' dead.
[HOTOKEDA]
Hey, sweetheart.
[KUROI gasps]
[HOTOKEDA] 'Scuse the timin',
but our organization
could seriously use
a lady of your talents.
Hmph.
Uh--!
Oh-ho! Look at that, huh?
Papa's startin' to get
the hang o' this!
Huh...
Y'know, I can't believe
it's the first time
this thought's
occurred to me, but...
Maybe we oughta cash in!
We're not gonna be a freak show.
We put ourselves out there,
they'll call us monsters.
[sighs]
[CLASS chattering]
[RINKA sighs]
He's probably right.
Hey there. How you doin'?
[RINKA gasps]
[RINKA yelps]
It's such a beautiful day.
Why don't we go eat
lunch together outside?
Shut up! Is this your boyfriend?
Somebody likes to
go after the older men,
doesn't she?
That's our girl!
[RINKA]
Shut up!
[KYOTARO]
First things first.
We keep our eyes peeled
for wrong-doing
and intervene whenever possible.
It'll help raise
esper awareness.
We'll get the public onboard
with seeing us as an asset.
Next, we persuade
the police to give us
a cool call sign or a
direct line to headquarters.
[RINKA]
Um. Not really followin' ya.
[KYOTARO]
Well, clearly I'm the strategist
and you're the brawn
of the operation.
And together we fight crime!
[sighs] Yeah, sure.
What could possibly go wrong?
But aren't you excited?
Actually, now that you
mention it, no, I'm not.
I don't wanna use
my powers to fight crime,
I want them gone!
[KYOTARO] Hm. I suppose my
assumption the fish chose
you specifically was incorrect.
[KYOTARO] But why is it
that some people can see them
while others can't?
Are they just
governed by chance,
like all natural phenomena?
Or could they be some kind of
randomly generated hologram.
How would I go about
trying to find them again?
[KYOTARO] It just so happens
I have a lead.
They seem to have
a natural predator.
Find the penguin. Find the fish.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 3A]
Attenton please.
Next stop,
Shibarua-futo Station.
[EDOYAMA] We do not
keep pets in this house.
If you have time to
take care of an animal.
You have time to read.
I don't care.
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 3A]
This is unprecedented!
The first of its species to fly!
[KYOTARO] Apparently they're
indigenous to South America
and prefer to make
their nests on cliff-faces
overlookin' the ocean.
So what does that tell ya?
That this is as good
a place to start as any?
[KYOTARO]
Bingo.
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 3A] Stay put,
you little aberration, you.
Keep those fins where
they are, this is for science.
[PEGGY squeaks]
And a substantial run
on the talk-show circuit.
Make a break for it, Peggy!
[MALE CLUB MEMBERS gasp]
[PEGGY squeals]
Heads up! There it is!
Wait, what the hell?
[screams]
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 3C]
No sweat, boys!
Little Birdie's in the nest!
[RINKA]
Right! Let's do this!
[KYOTARO grunts]
I'm not gonna let you
do anything to my Peggy!
Uh, fellahs,
she's talkin' to me.
Stay out of this, young lady.
Fat chance of that, creep!
Quit bein' an ass-pain
and hand over the squawker!
No! This is kidnapping!
Pull over right now!
[PEGGY sqeaks]
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 3A groans]
[KYOTARO]
You're up, Rinka. Stay focused.
I got this.
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 3B]
Knock it off!
Hurry! Grab my hand!
[ALL yell]
Get us out of here!
[KYOTARO]
How many people inside?
I think it's just three.
[MALE CLUB MEMBERS yelling]
[OLD LADIES gasping]
Kyotaro!
[OLD LADIES yelp]
[KYOTARO] Okay, teleporting
a van might've been pushing it.
I can't even wiggle my toes now.
Don't tell me this is
how I'm gonna go out.
[KYOTARO]
And I was just starting
to get somewhere with her, too.
We were... friends?
[PEGGY whining]
[MURASAKI]
I saw Peggy for the first time
on the way home from school.
I was sitting on the train,
nose in a book.
[PEGGY cooing]
Oh!
Here you go, sweetie,
bon appétit.
[PEGGY cooing]
Peggy is very special.
He's my only friend
in the whole world.
My dad doesn't approve of pets.
[MURASAKI]
But after what happened today,
I need to think of a new plan
for this little guy.
What if he comes
to live with me?
And maybe you keep
what you know about me
and my friend on the D.L.
I imagine it'd cause quite
a stir if people knew
about the two of you.
[RINKA]
Yeah. No joke.
You guys are the coolest
people I've ever met!
You're like super heroes
or something!
[KYOTARO]
Hm.
She thinks we're like heroes.
[KYOTARO] Well, you do
have a lot of potential
in that area, you know.
Look, you're very sweet, but...
The vigilante thing
isn't my bag.
Let me ask you something, Rinka.
Do you know what it's like to
live every day without hope?
[CROWD gasps]
[KYOTARO]
Where I grew up,
if you were at the bottom of the
food chain, that's how it was.
The idea of a hero was
an unfathomable concept
to me when I was a kid.
But, then...
Meeting you six months ago
changed all that.
It's like...
For the first time in
my life, I knew hope.
Anyway, see ya tomorrow.
We met six months ago?
[PEGGY]
Wah!
[MALE ANNOUNCER 3A] Dramatic
accident on Rainbow Bridge
this afternoon.
Witnesses claim to have seen
a man in a crow-like mask
accompanied by a
mysterious albino girl,
both said to have used
some sort of, quote: "super"...
[RINKA groans]
We've gone through
this whole bag of rice!
What'll we do?
I don't get paid again
until next week!
[RINDOU]
Rinka.
This white-haired girl
everybody's up in arms about
is you, isn't it?
[RINKA]
Huh?
I wasn't sure at first,
but it looked like
she was saving
this little girl from
some creepy dudes in a van.
Well, and then the
guy in the weird mask
saved those old ladies,
which was totally awesome!
The long and short of it is,
whoever they are,
I owe them my life.
Okay, before you
start freaking out.
We weren't doing anything bad,
just giving some folks a hand--
[RINDOU]
Damn it, Rinka!
[KYOTARO] Well, naturally
he's gonna worry.
He's your dad.
And you make no effort
to disguise yourself.
Oh, whatever.
My hair goes white,
what more do you want?
[MURASAKI]
I think the publicity is great.
People are crazy about you guys.
[BOY 3A]
Oh crap, it's her!
[BOY 3B]
Let's get out of here!
[KYOTARO]
Friends of yours, I'm guessing?
[MURASAKI] Just some boys
from the neighborhood.
[MURASAKI] My house is
just around the corner
if you wanna head back.
We're cool with walking you
the rest of the way home.
It's probably better
we know where you live,
just in case.
[RINKA]
Whoa!
Not to be rude, but is
your family, like, loaded?
That's not exactly it, no.
[MALE SUBORDINATES]
Welcome home,
young mistress Murasaki.
That wasn't quite the welcome
I was expecting to get.
[EDOYAMA]
This is a rare pleasure.
[KYOTARO, RINKA]
Uh--
[EDOYAMA] Friends of my
daughter, you honor me.
Welcome to our home.
[MURASAKI] I should've
said something before.
It's just that most people
get weird about it
and I didn't want
to scare you guys off.
Don't worry. It's okay.
I don't expect to be liked.
[RINKA]
We're not gonna blame you
for who your parents are.
C'mon. Give us a little credit.
[MURASAKI]
Thank you.
[RINKA] And since they
went to all this trouble
we might as well eat, right?
[MURASAKI] Yup! There's
more where this came from!
[RINKA]
Woo hoo!
[HOTOKEDA] It's been awhile
hasn't it, Boss Edoyama?
You're Hotokeda,
if memory serves.
What brings you here
all of a sudden?
[HOTOKEDA]
Well...
I figured I'd try to be a
gentleman, give you the courtesy
of a quiet takeover
without all the fuss
of an all-out turf war.
I see.
Think I'll just give you the
Kanto region, is that it?
Yeah, that's more
or less the idea.
I'll spare you the details,
but we've come up in the world.
[KUROI]
I'm gonna take a leak.
Ugh.
I'm not the biggest fan of
yakuza, but this fat bastard's
scummier than most of 'em.
[RINKA] Got it. Down the hall,
and to the right.
Uh--
Hm?
[RINKA, KUROI scream]
Uh...?
Wait, shouldn't you be in jail?
[KYOTARO]
Is something wrong, or...?
[MURASAKI, PEGGY]
Hm?
[HOTOKEDA]
Well, it's about that time.
[MURASAKI yelps]
[KYOTARO grunts]
[MURASAKI grunts]
Help! Rinka!
[RINKA]
Murasaki!
[RINKA grunts]
Guess who's suddenly
a big believer in karma?
[RINKA grunting, panting]
[KUROI]
I mean...
You can't ignore coincidence.
What's goin' on out there?
[HOTOKEDA]
Nothing all that special.
Simple kidnapping
via teleportation.
[MURASAKI, KYOTARO grunt]
--[KYOTARO grunts]
--Kyotaro!
[PEGGY]
Wah!
Peggy, no!
[HOTOKEDA]
There's no need for you to worry
about your girl.
We'll take care of her.
You just think things over.
Take your time.
[EDOYAMA growls]
[KUROI grunts]
[RINKA grunts]
Why aren't her punches
passing through me?
[KUROI] Looks like your power's
got some limits to it, babe.
Heh.
Walls you can pass through,
people not so much.
Life's a bitch, princess.
Now you tell me.
[RINKA grunts]
I've had just about
enough of you!
What the--?
Yeah, 'bout that.
One of the details I was
hopin' to skip over
in the interest
of doin' business.
What the hell are you?
I'm the guy who can give ya
everything ya want. So hand over
the Kanto Territory.
And not only do you
get your daughter back,
I'll sell ya super powers
for a cool ten mill.
It's a short term offer
and your daughter's life
is on the line, so I imagine
you'll wanna decide
'fore too long.
[KYOTARO grunts]
[MURASAKI grunts]
[MURASAKI]
Let go! Kyotaro!
[WINGED MASK]
Don't get involved, Kyotaro.
She's not worth it.
[KYOTARO]
Murasaki!
It's weird, but I feel like
I know who that kidnapper is.
Wait. This...
This is our apartment building.
[KUROI] Huh. So your name
is Rinka Urushiba.
[RINKA]
Uh--
You don't have to
go through with this!
Wish I could say
it's not personal.
But when you get down
to it, it kinda is.
Ha! Burn baby, burn!
[RINKA gasps]
Dad, get out of there!
[KUROI] Unless you want
more where that came from,
honey, I suggest you stay
out of my goddamn way.
[RINKA]
Daddy. I'm so sorry.
This is what happens
when I get involved.
It's my fault.
[RINKA sobbing]
The people close to me get hurt.
Who did I think I was?
[RINDOU yells]
Dad, you're okay!
[RINDOU] Somebody call
the fire department!
Thank goodness.
I thought I'd lost him.
[KYOTARO]
Oh my god!
[RINDOU]
Huh?
They didn't get you.
I'm so glad.
[KYOTARO gasps]
[YOUNG KYOTARO]
Paulo!
[YOUNG KYOTARO gasps]
Don't die on me! Please!
[RINDOU] Give me one
good reason I shouldn't
rearrange your face
for gettin' my daughter
mixed up in this crap!
[RINKA]
Stop it!
This isn't the time for
you to go all alpha male!
A little girl's been kidnapped.
We need a rescue plan!
[RINDOU grunts]
Well, if we knew who did it,
we'd have someplace to start.
[RINKA]
Hm...
If nothing else, we should
at least call the police,
don't you think?
Hotokeda! That was
the ringleader's name!
That's all we need to know!
That fat bastard runs
the scene in Otsuka.
[KYOTARO grunts]
I'll go take care of it.
You guys stay here.
[RINKA]
Are you kidding me?
Rinka! Sweetie!
[RINKA] This is my fault.
I should've protected her.
They got her because
I screwed up. I failed!
I'm not any kind of hero.
God! Look at me!
I can't even stand
on my own two feet!
[MERAYAMA]
In ya go!
Tell me where I am!
What're you people
gonna do to me?
I'll tell ya what we're gonna do
if you don't shut that whiny
little trap o' yours, sweet pea.
I'll burn ya so good,
they'll have to bust out
dental records to I.D. ya.
[KUROI] So ya think
ya can sell superpowers
to any schmo with a wad a' cash?
Cause it sounds bunk to me.
[HOTOKEDA]
You won't care how it sounds
once the money
starts rollin' in.
But how's it even possible?
These little fish
are about to be
the hottest commodity
you've ever seen.
People'll lose their
minds over 'em.
All we need is
someone on the street
who knows how to push product.
[HOTOKEDA]
Merayama.
Go check out our new digs.
Kill anyone from the old guard.
I don't want any legacy costs.
[MERAYAMA]
Right.
[MERAYAMA gasps]
[MERAYAMA] You do all this
on your own, little birdie?
[KYOTARO] Tell me where
you're keeping the girl.
I've got no time for games.
[MERAYAMA]
You think it's that simple?
Clockin' a few guys
ain't enough incentive.
[KYOTARO]
Tell me where she is, dammit!
[MERAYAMA]
Ugh. Knock it off, kid.
Look at'cha. You ain't
held a gun before.
[MERAYAMA gasps]
[MERAYAMA groans]
[KYOTARO]
That was a warning shot.
Your kind has no surprises
in store for me.
Not since I was kid.
[MERAYAMA panting]
So you prepared for this?
This is some serious bullshit!
How the hell am I
s'posed to dodge a guy
who blips in and out
of thin air?
[MERAYAMA grunts]
Watch where you're goi--!
Long time no see, Merayama.
Oh shit! Old Man Urushiba!
You burn my apartment building
down, you son of a bitch?
I got no idea what
you're talkin' about,
I swear it!
[RINDOU]
Tell us where the girl is
or I'll launch your
sorry ass into orbit!
Don't test me, ya little shit!
Thank goodness you're okay!
Little out of character for you.
Since when do
super heroes need guns?
Depends on the people
they're up against.
And it depends on
what's at stake.
Whatever you say, I guess.
[MURASAKI whimpering]
[MURASAKI grunting]
[MURASAKI]
Stop being a child for once.
You're always such
a stupid liability.
Kyotaro!
[PEGGY]
Wah!
Peggy, no!
Gotta be strong.
You've gotta stand up and get
yourself outta this mess!
[KUROI] I'm gonna go
out on a limb and guess
you're not exactly
from around here.
The hell is that rock anyway?
That how you caught all the
fish, or is that a trade secret?
[WINGED MASK]
There's no need for you to know.
The fish do what they please.
They decide everything.
Huh?
[MURASAKI screams]
[RINDOU] Alright. This is where
the sons a' bitches hide out.
Kid.
Get my daughter outta here
and take her to the bar.
I'll save the girl. Bastards
won't see Rindou comin'!
Dad, you can't
do this by yourself.
Some of those guys are espers!
I can't just sit and wait
for you to come back
when I know you're
in over your head.
[RINDOU]
Give your old man some credit.
Try giving your daughter
some credit for once!
You didn't train me
to be a bystander!
Had to play that card.
At least you come by that
pig-headedness honestly.
[RINKA grunts]
Now take her to the bar
like I asked you.
Cut it out!
[RINKA]
Oh! No way!
Don't just stare.
You got enough juice left to
teleport me inside or what?
You and your father
have some issues.
[RINKA]
Shut up.
Do we or don't we
have a responsibility?
You really want us to be heroes?
Then we gotta move, now!
What's gotten into you?
Murasaki. We're saving her.
[PEGGY] Scene Four:
The Rain, Ring, and Girl.