'Cept the hot ones
never go for nice.
[WOMAN]
Kagura! Over here!
Huh?
[panting]
Ugh... Way to
show up on time, Yomi.
Sorry. I got here
as soon as I could.
A call came through
that just couldn't wait.
And I guess it's too much
to ask that you text me?
[YOMI]
Hey, don't be like that.
I come bearing gifts.
Huh?
Fine.
[BOTH chuckle softly]
So, uh, we okay?
[KAGURA]
Yeah, yeah, let's go.
[KYOTARO]
There's an old saying...
S'posed to be pretty cool.
That's what I hear.
[KAGURA laughs]
[KYOTARO] "You can live
your life one of two ways."
[KYOTARO]
You can slog through
believing that
miracles don't exist.
[KYOTARO] Or you can
take it as a fact
that everything's a miracle.
[rumbling]
[MALE CAPTAIN 1A]
Give me a status report!
Yes, sir!
Captain, look!
[MALE CAPTAIN 1A]
What the hell?
[MALE SOLDIER 1B] Sir.
It's the parliament building!
For those of you out there
just tuning in,
we've received confirmation
that the Parliament Building
has been hijacked
by a group of espers.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 1A]
The building itself is currently
suspended above
the downtown skyline.
Area traffic will be redir--
[PROFESSOR] Season's Greetings
denizens of Tokyo.
[PROFESSOR] As of this
fine winter's evening,
your illustrious metropolis
will be under new management.
[CROWD gasping]
[PROFESSOR] I'm afraid the
issue is not up for debate.
Anyone who wishes to survive...
is advised to
get on their knees.
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE 1A]
Don't move! You will be shot!
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE
1A, 1B gasp]
1A, 1B scream]
The plight of the complacent.
Peace makes knaves
and dullards of us all.
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE 1C grunts]
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE 1D groans]
Our eyes are only ever fully
open when faced with terror.
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE
1C, 1D gasp]
And they who rule
in ignorance court oblivion.
[MALE PROFESSOR GUARD 1A grunts]
[chimes, door lock clicks]
What the hell?
Try aiming
a bit to the left.
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE 1F grunts]
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE 1G groans]
[PROFESSOR]
Well, that didn't work.
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE 1H groans]
[CROWD gasps]
Dear oh dear.
I do seem to get around.
[MALE SPECIAL SERVICE
1E, 1I groan]
Everyone in this room
is a hostage.
So you'll remain...
until your constituents
relinquish the reins
to better hands.
[MALE POLICE 1A]
Ladies and gentlemen, please!
Evacuate in a calm
and orderly fashion!
Fantastic. Move it, assholes,
I got places to be.
[MALE ESPER 1A]
You're not the only one.
[gasps]
[MALE TAXI DRIVER 1A]
Oh, uh. Thanks.
[CROWD gasps]
There's been an explosion
in front of Yotsuya.
I need a fire brigade, stat.
[MALE ESPER 1A laughs intensely]
[CROWD screams]
[MALE TV STAFF 1A]
Where's our goddamn chopper?
She's fueling up, chief!
Gimme half an hour!
[FEMALE TV STAFF 1A]
Uh, guys?
Apparently there's
bombs going off now?
[MALE TV STAFF 1A]
Are you kidding me?
What? They hit
Roppongi Hills?
Holy shit!
[MALE OFFICIAL 1A]
So what do we do?
The hostages factor out walking
in through the front door.
[MALE OFFICIAL 1B]
We can't launch an offensive
until they're
out of harm's way.
[MALE OFFICIAL 1C] And I can't
assemble a rescue team
with all my men
out there chasing fires!
[MALE OFFICIAL 1D] What are
we paying the police for?
[MALE OFFICIAL 1E] Do we have
any intel on these people?
Right. I want the PDC
put on this immediately.
Division One is en route with
countermeasure artillery, sir.
Send in Division Four!
[alarm blares]
[MALE ANNOUNCER 1A]
Breaking news this hour.
Several explosions have
rippled throughout Tokyo,
believed to be the work
of the same terrorists
holding the Parliament
Building hostage.
Police give no
comments as to motive,
but are cautioning
residents to stay alert.
As the explosions
appear to be cropping up
more or less at random.
It's hard to substantiate
this right now, of course.
But the alleged
ringleader behind
these acts of terrorism
is believed to be the same man
responsible for last June's
tanker incident in Tokyo.
Citizens in districts
under evacuation
are urged to cooperate
with emergency personnel
and move in an orderly fashion
toward designated shelters.
Huh?
[train horn blares]
That puts espers at one.
Mankind, zero!
Okay, well.
Hopefully this
gives you some idea.
As you can see,
the scope of the damage
is just unbelievable, and
things continue to escalate--
Whoa! That was
another explosion!
[MALE POLICE 1C] Don't panic!
I repeat, do not panic!
I hate to say it, but...
...this reporter sees
no alternative
to giving the terrorists
whatever they want.
With the so-called
"White Girl" MIA,
how can normal humans
hope to stand against them?
Who can possibly
defend us in her place?
She'll make a move soon,
I know it!
How do you know
she wasn't quarantined
by the new ESP legislation?
[helicopter blades hum]
New development, folks!
Some kind of special.
I assume military plane
is bearing down
on the Parliament Building.
With any luck I ruled out
the White Girl too soon.
Perhaps she and
her remarkable associates
are here to save the day!
All right, listen up!
First, our primary concern
is the hostages.
Meaning stealth.
We rope down like ghosts.
Second, our enemy is powerful.
We're talking espers
with an axe to grind.
I shouldn't have to tell you--
[groans]
[DIVISION 1 SOLDIER 1A]
Captain!
You'll pay for that!
She isn't onboard.
[FEMALE REPORTER 1A gasps]
[TORU] Freeze. Why's a cute
little thing like you
wielding a pair of katana?
I said freeze!
[TORU gasps]
We've got a live one.
[TORU]
If you're feeling frisky,
by all means, try your luck.
[gasps]
Huh?
[grunts lightly]
Agent Seventy-seven to HQ.
Staring down
an esper as I speak.
[MAMI] Copy, Seventy-seven.
The orders haven't changed.
All espers are
to be terminated
with extreme
prejudice on sight.
The higher-ups
have declared open season.
Fire to your heart's content.
[radio static]
That makes things
simple, I guess.
[radio beeping]
[MASAKI] Agent Fifty-five
to Seventy-seven.
You're comin' in
loud and clear.
What's up, Masaki?
[MASAKI]
According to my records,
the girl you're
facing off with is one of
the Professor's lackeys.
You might wanna
capture her alive.
[TORU] No guarantees.
She's a Teleporter.
I'll be lucky to
capture her at all.
--Here's the plan.
--[NATSUKI] Yeah?
On my signal
I'm gonna need you
to aim your bike
at the target.
Sure thing.
I don't know what you think
that'll accomplish, but okay.
[TORU]
Just trust me.
Dismount and let 'er fly!
Good work, Natsuki!
What does he not understand
about "capture alive"?
Please continue
to watch over us.
I seriously loved that bike.
Yeah, I know.
Take an I.O.U.?
Please return, Minami.
[PROFESSOR]
No need for haste.
Our friend will
show herself in due time.
[MINAMI]
Right.
Uh... The hell
are we starin' at?
[PROFESSOR chuckles]
[NATSUKI gasps]
Okay, sure.
[TORU] These guys are
starting to piss me off.
[helicopter blades hums]
[MALE CAPTAIN 1B] Attention
all radicals occupying
the parliament building.
This government does not
negotiate with terrorists.
There will be no deals.
I repeat: no negotiations.
No deals. If you do not release
the hostages immediately
we will open fire.
[MALE CAPTAIN 1B]
This is your final warning.
You have to the count of five
to lay down your
weapons and surrender.
One. Two. Three.
[PROFESSOR] I was beginning
to wonder whether mankind
would bare its fangs. Heh.
[MALE SOLDIER 1C]
Huh?
[MALE SOLDIER 1C, 1E, 1D gasp]
[SALARY MAN 1A]
Damn espers!
We should've wiped them out
when we had the chance!
[GIRL 1A] Don't worry, Mom.
Big Sis will come, just wait.
[MOTHER 1A]
"Big Sis"?
Mm-hm.
--[GIRL 1A] Her.
--[MOTHER 1A] Oh.
She always shows up.
Whenever people
are hurt and need help,
the White Girl comes in
and saves the day!
Should I know
who she's talking about?
Some kind of hero, I think,
not sure if she's real.
The White Girl is very real.
She saved my best friend's life.
I saw it happen
with my own two eyes.
[GIRL 1A]
Really?
[SALARY MAN 1A] You think
she's comin' to save us?
Hell, far as I'm concerned
she's what we need savin' from!
Her kind are
a damned aberration!
Walk a mile in their shoes
and then see how you feel.
It's not fair to
write 'em all off.
Don't you worry,
she'll be here.
I know for a fact
she's not the type
to excuse herself from a fight.
You mean that?
Are you friends with her,
do you actually know her?
Hm.
He's full of shit.
Tell us another one, smartass.
She your girlfriend?
Even if she does
give a damn about us,
what the hell
is one girl gonna do?
She's not in this
by herself. Uh!
[AYUMU]
Murasaki!
[MURASAKI]
Ayumu!
What're you doing?
You actually came out
all this way on your own?
[MURASAKI]
Yeah.
I couldn't just sit there
and watch all this happen.
I don't suppose you know...
what they might've
done with Rinka?
Mm-mm.
Don't worry! C'mon,
you know how she is.
Nobody could ever
keep her down!
She's not gonna
just sit there either.
Yeah, you're right.
[MURASAKI]
Hey!
There's some good luck for us!
As long as I have one of these,
I can monitor
what they're planning!
Your psychometry trick
does come in handy.
Hold up, I'll go you
one better.
I know Peggy's still alive.
Where have you been tonight?
The city's a warzone and you're
taking in the freakin' sights?
[MURASAKI]
Sort of.
Don't "sort of" me!
What were we supposed to do
if something
happened to you?
And what if something
I told you I'm not
just gonna stay put.
It's not much,
but I'm doing what I can!
[AYUMU sighs]
[MURASAKI gasps]
[AYUMU]
What do you see?
They're gonna let it go!
They're gonna drop
the Parliament Building!
[MURASAKI]
Where are you going?
My mother's in there!
I've gotta get her out!
[GIRL 1A]
Are you still here?
Oh! There you are! Hey!
Is that that girl?
When you see Big Sis,
can you tell her something
for me? I just
want her to know...
that we all love her
very, very much!
Because of all of the nice
things that she does for us!
Tell her thanks! Okay?
[MURASAKI gasps]
[AYUMU yells]
[SALARY MAN 1A yells]
[AYUMU groans]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A]
Sorry 'bout that, normal peeps.
Are we all okay?
[laughs]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A] My goodness!
You're hardy as cockroaches!
Oh, well. Let's try again.
[beeping]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A]
In just five widdle minutes
I'm blowin' this place
to kingdom come!
[PEOPLE gasp]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A laughs]
Mommy!
Damn kid.
[FEMALE ESPER 1A gasps]
Not on my watch!
What the--?
Nuh-uh! Gotta keep
these darlings
sealed in for freshness!
[yelps]
Mommy, no! Mommy!
Get away from here, Nana!
Run far away!
[FEMALE ESPER 1A]
Oh, stop.
You are just breaking
my heart with this.
There, there, doll.
Don't you fret over mummsie.
She's about to be
her own constellation.
♪ Twinkle-twinkle little star! ♪
Uh. What is wrong with you?
These are people!
Drop this force field
and let them go!
I'll take it down.
About five seconds
before she goes boom.
I mean, I'm not ready
to meet my maker yet.
[AYUMU gasps]
Please, ya gotta
do something!
My mommy's in there!
Help us! Mommy!
Get her out of here!
Take my daughter
somewhere safe!
[sobbing]
Do this for me, please!
Mommy!
No! Let go of me!
We can't leave her in there!
[MURASAKI grunting]
[AYUMU]
Murasaki. What are you?
We gonna roll over
and take this?
I don't think so! Not today!
[MURASAKI grunting]
[AYUMU grunting]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A] Now this
is just getting awkward.
Use your head, kiddies:
the operative word here
is "force-field."
Put some "upmh" into it!
[laughing]
[KUROI]
Excellent advice.
Umph happens to be
my specialty.
And since you're
so hungry for it,
I'd be happy
to give you a taste.
[bellows]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A yells]
[FEMALE ESPER 1A grunts]
Nice, Kuroi!
That gave me enough time
to defuse the bomb.
[FEMALE ESPER 1A]
You what?!
[AYUMU]
Don't bother.
A gun's not gonna do
much against us.
I mean, at least...
...no more than it would you.
[FEMALE ESPER 1A]
Well son of a bitch.
Every damn one
of you's an esper?
[CROWD murmurs]
[KUROI] Ugh. Okay, let's not
argue about this right now,
and just agree that
not all of us are bad.
Sure, some espers are rotten.
But who was the
first person to step up
the last time things got ugly?
You know where
I'm goin' with this.
That idiot with the
heart of gold.
[bellows]
[ESPER E grunts, yells]
[MALE SOLDIER 1F, 1G yell]
[MALE ESPER 1B yells]
[MALE CAPTAIN 1C]
We're in over our heads!
Full retreat! Now!
[ESPER E]
Huh...?
[bellows]
[ESPER E grunts]
[RINKA]
Skull-Crushing... Psy-Kick!
[PROFESSOR] At long last.
The hero has come.
Urushiba.
[PEGGY]
Scene Two: "Girl Meets Boy!"