[AMAMIKU]
I'm your friend. Ai.
[HARUKA gasps]
Ai Amamiku Hasebe.
You can't be... Ai...
It's 15 years in the future.
From your timeline.
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA] 15 years later?
This is... our future?
[YUKIE] I've had enough
of this nonsense!
I just don't find it amusing!
Filling my student's heads
with your ridiculous ideas
and scaring them!
[UCHIDA]
I'm tellin' you the truth!
Haruka happens to be
one of my students!
If she really has gone missing,
I will be the one
to find her! Not you!
Ugh! Look, if she has vanished
because of the tunnel effect,
there is no way you can
possibly find her!
Tunnel effect? What are
you babbling on about?
Well, that doesn't make
any sense at all, does it?
And that is why I
keep repeatin' myself!
There is a possibility
Haruka encountered
a quantum phenomenon.
And I'm telling you
that makes no sense.
Huh?
This old bag is loopy.
[UCHIDA growls]
What did you say?! I happen
to be only 26 years old!
I guess your cheap makeup
must make you look that bad.
[UCHIDA] Oh, and I suppose you
like lookin' like a bag lady?!
[YUKIE] Ha, don't even
go there, grandma!
Ms. Yukie...
[AI growls]
[ISAMI gasps]
You know, come to think of it,
didn't Haruka say she thought
someone was after her?
[ISAMI]
Huh?
[YU] So it wasn't
me they were after...
They were after
Haruka all along.
Wait, who was after Haruka?
[YU]
I don't know...
I just don't know who it is!
[BOTH gasp]
What is it?
[UCHIDA]
Here.
Look, I am not sayin' that you
should trust me right away,
but if anything should ever
come up, please call me.
Wait just a minute!
[UCHIDA] Kooriyama, I'm going to
search this area a little more.
[KOORIYAMA]
Whatever you say.
What the hell is up with her?
"Federal Bureau...
of Intelligence"?!
[ISAMI]
Yu, wait up!
Hang on a minute!
Where do you think you're going?
Haruka's gone.
I just gotta find her.
[ISAMI]
Hey...
[KOSAGI]
Kuina.
I will be the one
to eliminate Karasu.
If we were to do nothing,
then we would be disgracing
the Dragon Knights.
He must be dealt
with immediately.
Why is it that you're always
thinking about Karasu?
What are you implying?!
Just forget about it.
Has Fukuro returned?
[KOSAGI] Yes, I'm sure
he's with his old friend.
[LILY]
Haruka's really strange.
Lily, please do not try to go up
to the surface any more, okay?
[LILY]
Please don't tell my mom, okay?
Sure, we wouldn't wanna make
her worry needlessly, would we?
[LILY]
Yeah, that's right.
There she is now! Mom!
[LILY] Hey, you've known my mom
for a long time, haven't you?
Yes, I sure have. Ever since
we were about your age.
I heard once that
when she was young,
you guys used to have a friend
who's name was Haruka!
Isn't that the
strangest thing ever?
Because now I have a friend
with the exact same name.
[HARUKA]
Is this really our future?
What happened to
everything on the surface?
How come the whole world
ended up like this?!
Come on, Ai. Please tell me.
[AMAMIKU] In your dimension,
5 years from your present time,
there was a
world-wide revolution.
It all began in our town.
[HARUKA]
Our town?
[AMAMIKU] You're still
too young to understand.
You can't comprehend
the significance
of the state of de-coherence
occurring in the ordinary world,
which was thought to be possible
only in the quantum world.
What's "de-coherence"? I don't
understand big words like that.
Where are Miho, Yu, and Isami?
They should all be in
this world too, right?
Even if your friends
are still actually alive,
they will have nothing
to do with you or your world.
I don't get it!
Isn't this our future?
[AMAMIKU] This is only one of
an infinite number of futures.
For you, this is
one possible future.
For us, you are one
option from the past.
So it is the future,
but it isn't the future.
[AMAMIKU]
That's right. You do exist.
But to us, it is quite
possible that you do not.
[HARUKA]
But how can that be?!
I'm standing right here,
and you're standing over there!
Perhaps you're still too young
to comprehend the concept
of multi-dimensional time, but
it is the truth of the Universe.
[AMAMIKU] The future,
the past, and even the present
only exist within chaos.
None of this makes
sense to me...
But I know one thing for sure.
You and I are both right here.
No, Haruka!
[HARUKA] It's all right.
If it will save you.
[KARASU grunting]
Karasu...
I know you tried to protect
the Dragon Torque from Atori.
[KOSAGI] Atori was attempting
to eliminate the Dragon Torque
from that dimension.
That was the source
of the Gestalt collapse,
isn't that correct?
I'll protect her
with my very life.
Ugh. The Haruka we know is dead!
That Haruka is from
a different dimension
than the one we're from.
It's definitely our past.
[KOSAGI]
You're wrong!
No matter how much it resembles
the world of your past,
it is merely an illusion!
That dimension is a
fantasy world that exists
because we transported
ourselves to it!
[KOSAGI grunts]
[KOSAGI crying]
[MIHO] I bet that those 2
are with secret intelligence.
You know, that
Majestic Twelve thing.
[ISAMI]
What's that?
[MIHO] They investigate alien
life, haven't you heard of it?
[ISAMI]
Why would I?
Oh, I don't know,
maybe because aliens have
finally come to invade Earth?
I highly doubt that.
It's true, Isami!
Aliens have been known to remove
internal organs from cows,
ya know?! Whoa! That's it!
Haruka was abducted
by some aliens!
This isn't something we
should joke about, Miho!
Hey, I'm not joking
about this, you guys!
I'm really worried about Haruka!
Ms. Yukie, what do you
think we should do?
[YUKIE] You haven't been able
to reach her on her cellphone?
[AI] No, it goes
right into voicemail.
She forgets her phone a lot.
[MIHO]
I'm worried!
It's already seven...
[ISAMI]
That's impossible!
[MIHO]
No, it can really happen!
Where in the world
are you, Haruka?!
[HARUKA] I wonder what the
Haruka in this dimension does.
[KUINA grunting]
[KUINA]
It's too difficult to do...!
[KUINA gasps]
[NOEIN]
The Dragon Torque must not
fall into the hands of La'cryma.
I know all this.
[NOEIN] You want to go
to Shangri-la, don't you?
That is correct. I wish to
escape from the ring fo destiny.
[NOEIN]
Your destiny... is cursed...
Both your past,
and your future...
That is precisely why
you may achieve salvation
only if you come to Shangri-la.
[KUINA grunting, groaning]
[KUINA]
Shangri... la...
[whistling]
[FUKURO] I'm surprised
to see you down here
in the Dragon's lair.
[AMAMIKU] Lily looks as if
she's doing quite well.
Yeah, she sure has her mother's
outgoing personality.
They act so similar
to one another,
it's hard to tell
'em apart sometimes.
I'm starting to have
doubts about our plan.
[FUKURO]
Hm?
The girl is far too similar
to the Haruka we know
from our dimension.
She's supposed to be similar.
We got her from
a parallel world.
Are we going to end up turning
our backs on her once again?
[FUKURO] Try not to think
about it, Amamiku.
It'll only create
more confusion.
It's Shangri-la!
[OPERATOR]
Uroboros formation confirmed.
There is an order breach.
Shangri-la is
corroding La'cryma.
[ENRA]
Why is this happening now?
[GOKAN] Once we have
obtained the Dragon Torque,
it will create for us
a perfect defense shield.
[TAIZA] With that,
we'll achieve success.
[GOKAN]
Yes. We will be successful.
As long as there are
no further errors.
Ventora, Ventora,
space people, please answer.
space people...
Miho, can we please
stop this right now?
We have to get them to return
Haruka, so chant with me!
We don't know for sure
it was aliens!
[YUKIE] Ventora, Ventora,
space people, please hear
our desperate pleas and
answer us right away!
Ventora, Ventora...
[ISAMI]
Ms. Yukie believes in this crap?
Now I've seen everything.
[HARUKA gasps]
Haruka...!
Where the hell are you?!
[MAN whispering]
You think that guy's okay?
[WOMAN whispering]
He looks really sick...
[MAN] Maybe I should
go get someone, huh?
[YU] Give her back!
Bring Haruka back to me!
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA] You don't have
to worry about it. Goodbye.
Thank you for
everything, Karasu.
[KARASU sputtering]
[WOMAN 1] Life reaction,
Reizu reaction, all normal.
[WOMAN 2] Quantum computer link,
active and stable.
What are your instructions,
Lady Amamiku?
Please commence plan.
[KARASU sputtering]
[KARASU panting]
Haruka!
What's happening?
What're you doing to me?
There's water coming in!
Let me outta here, now!
[muffled]
Let me out!
Please, let me out of here!
[OPERATOR] Shangri-la
Destructons in place.
Coordinates sent.
Dragon Knights mobilized.
[MAN gasps]
[KARASU panting]
[DRAGON KNIGHTS screaming]
[FUKURO grunts]
Readings stable.
Proceed to phase 2.
What's... going on?
Oh, Yu.
Haruka?!
Where are you?!
Haruka!
[KARASU grunting]
[KOSAGI grunts]
Ugh! They've
reached the surface!
[KUINA]
It's crying...
Help me--!
[AMAMIKU gasps]
[HARUKA]
Am I going to die...?
Will I ever see
my friends again...?
Yu, I wish I could've
seen you one more time...
[WOMAN 1] The Dragon
Torque has appeared.
[WOMAN 2] Beginning elementary
particalization reaction.
[WOMAN 3]
Entropy rising.
[AMAMIKU gasps]
[AMAMIKU]
Karasu!
[FUKURO yells]
You came to my rescue...
Oh, Yu...
[WOMAN gasps]
Why are you doing this, Karasu?!
Why are you going to let
La'cryma become extinct?!
[KARASU]
I will protect Haruka.
I don't ever want
to lose her again.
[HARUKA gasps]
What happened?
[AMAMIKU] If you choose
to protect that girl,
you could very well
lose your own existence.
It doesn't matter.
I will be her protector
for as long as I exist.
[AMAMIKU]
Haruka...
I'm very sorry.
It's alright.
[OPERATOR] Dimensions stabilizer
restored. Limes reconstructed.
[FUKURO groans]
I refuse to allow our
world to end just yet...
[KARASU]
Hold on tight to me.
[YU panting]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
Haruka!
[HARUKA] You're Karasu.
You're Yu in the future!
[KUINA] We will get rid
of him, you understand?!
[HARUKA]
Next, "Secrets."
Will you keep it quiet?