[KOSAGI] Karasu and the
others disappeared?!
To be precise, I completely
deleted their data.
Give me a minute while I
reconstruct the program.
How could that occur?!
Yelling at me isn't
going to help much.
Is he dead?
Tell me he isn't dead!
[TOBI] Don't jump to any
conclusions, Kosagi.
And keep your voice down;
we really don't want
Haruka's mother to hear this.
We're counting on you, so bring
our friends back already.
Haruka will be okay, won't she?
[MIHO]
Atori...
[ATORI] Hmm? So what are
you looking at me for?
Do you think there's any chance
we'll get them back here?
I don't know but I guess it
can't hurt to try, right?
Atori, stop talking like that!
We're all worried about them
and your bad attitude
certainly isn't helping us
deal with it any better!
Uh, Miho...!
If you're from the future too,
then how come
you're not helping?!
Idiot!
Atori?
I really don't have
the skills for that.
Huh?
Dimensional operations
are Tobi's expertise.
I would just be getting in
the way if I tried to help.
Well, I guess that explains it.
Okay, Atori, you're forgiven.
You can come over
here by me now.
Alright, I will.
Dammit. He's up to something.
He hasn't completely
reverted back yet.
[KOSAGI]
That may be, but--
So, you don't have
to worry about it.
What is it now?
It's really nothing.
I just have to hurry.
[YU] He called it by
the name "Shangri-la."
I wonder if this might
be another future for us.
Another what?
I don't really understand
it myself, but...
You know what, Karasu?
Maybe that guy who wears
the mask is really...
Alright, so just what are
we supposed to do now?
Looks like this fog is getting
a lot thicker all of a sudden.
It might be dangerous
to stick around.
We should probably leave.
I think you may be right.
I can barely make out a thing.
We need to get out of here, now.
Um, okay...
[YU]
C'mon, let's go, Haruka.
Hey, stop! Wait a minute.
[YU] Hold on to my hand
so we don't get split up.
Oh, Karasu.
[HARUKA]
I can't see a thing.
[YU] If this gets worse,
we won't even be able to see
where we're going.
What you can see with your eyes
has no meaning in this place.
What d'you mean?
This entire dimension
is merely an illusion.
[YU]
An illusion, huh?
[KARASU]
For both of you, in this world,
your existence has yet
to be established.
[YU]
Sorry, I don't get it.
What's that supposed to mean?
[KARASU] This dimension is a
parallel dimension to La'cryma
which means it is the future
from your point of view.
The future?
It is but one of
several possible futures.
But even if this world is
an illusion, you're still here.
And so's Karasu.
And because you're
both here, I'm here too.
And I couldn't be happier.
I think it's completed.
[AI]
Whoa!
Tobi, does this represent
dimensional construction?
I'm impressed,
Ms. Uchida, really.
The infinite number
of dimensions
that hypothetically exist
have a mutual link.
This graphic represents
that in real time.
It's the coordinates of
a particular dimension.
I can only make a
simplified version
with the calculating power
of the systems I have here,
but we should still be
able to use it to find out
whether Haruka exists.
All I have to do is
input her data and...
That's her. She's alright;
Haruka definitely
still exists somewhere.
So where is she?
[TOBI] I believe...
that she's in Shangri-la.
[phone rings]
This is Uchida speakin'.
[MAYUZUMI] Nice to talk to you.
My name is Mayuzumi.
Dr. Mayuzumi?
[MAYUZUMI] I heard about you
from Professor Sasaki.
[UCHIDA]
Where are you right now, Doctor?
[MAYUZUMI] I'm here in
the same town as you.
[UCHIDA]
What?
[MAYUZUMI]
Listen, can we meet right now?
There's something I need
to discuss with you.
It's important.
[KOORIYAMA]
Uchida, where are you going?!
[UCHIDA]
Ah, to talk to Dr. Mayuzumi!
I see something...
What is that?
[YU]
What's with this town?
Has it been abandoned?
This town is really
weirding me out.
[KARASU] This town doesn't
really exist. It's an illusion.
[YU]
Not that again.
[TIME DRIFTER]
Haruka...
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[TIME DRIFTER]
You must be very careful.
This is a wavering town, a place
where your soul will waver,
and judgement will be bent.
You musn't lose sight
of the future you desire.
Hey, are you okay?
What's wrong, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
Yeah... I'm okay...
She must be exhausted.
Let's take a break for now.
That works for me.
[YU] It looks real.
There are rooms and everything.
[HARUKA] Do you think...
somebody lived here?
[HARUKA]
Not even a soul...
[YU]
This place should be safe.
Why don't you go lie down?
At least there's a bed in here.
Take care of yourself, Haruka.
Yeah...
[YU]
It's okay, just get some rest.
[HARUKA]
Mm-hmm...
[YU] So what's next?
What do we do now?
I knew it. You don't
have a clue, do ya?
We should rest while
there's still time.
[UCHIDA] They've progressed
further than I thought.
[KOORIYAMA]
So you think it's ready to go?
[UCHIDA] They're waitin'
for the green light.
So is that him?
That's him, let's go.
[UCHIDA]
Dr. Mayuzumi, I presume?
You must be Miss Uchida.
I guess the rumors were true.
I've read your dissertation
on the critical stages
of quantum potential.
You've outlined a very
interesting concept--
Doctor, the Magic
Circle Experiment
must be stopped at all costs!
I know, it's just... well, I--
If a massive enough quantity
of the theta particles
generated from the
Magic Circle becomes linked,
there is the
distinct possibility
that a powerful place
sight will be generated.
That phenomenon is something
that can only occur
if it goes critical.
Please look at this.
This contains a map of this
region's quantum potential.
As you can see, this region
is exhibitin' the aspects
of a quantum waver.
If it reaches
a phaser criticality,
a dimensional contact
interference would occur.
That would mean
that all dimensions,
the entire universe,
may be wiped out.
What makes the quantum
potential of this region unique?
There is the possibility
that the existence of Haruka
is the cause and
effect of everything!
That can't be right!
[UCHIDA] Haruka may become
the proof for your theory!
Which means, mankind's
unique quantum makeup
is the reason the phenomenon of
unstable quantum worlds
has become established!
Our existence
establishes the others!
Mankind is the root
of the universe,
which is composed of
overlappin' dimensions,
and is the center
of the network.
That is your theory, right?
But it all may be destroyed
by the Magic Circle Project!
[KOORIYAMA]
Dr. Mayuzumi.
Correct me if I'm wrong, sir,
but it's not right for us
to destroy our
children's future.
[phone ringing]
Kaminogi residence, hello?
Takuya?
Huh?
Right now?
Haruka, I've gotta run
a quick errand!
Please watch the house
while I'm out, okay?
Uh, no problem we'll do it!
Well, where's Haruka?
She went to the store!
Oh. Well, take care
of things 'til I get back.
[AI]
Yes ma'am.
Do you think she
might be on to us?
No. We're in the clear for now.
Wanna pray? Should I pray?
[AI]
Shut up.
Tobi, tell me what is
that makes you believe
that Haruka is
in Shangri-la now.
There are signs
of her existence,
but I can't seem to
lock down which dimension.
Whichever one she's in,
it's in a state of instability.
I believe it's safe to say that
they transported to Shangri-la
because the dimension is in
a state of de-coherence.
So... where's this
"Shangrey-lah" place anyway?
[ATORI chuckling]
Atori?
Tobi, do a
fixed-reverse calculation
on the Dragon Torque's data.
The result should get
Shangri-la's position for us.
That would end
our troubles, yes?
That would be dangerous.
Shangri-la is known
to be unstable;
there is a risk Haruka
could disappear.
[ATORI]
Dammit! Stop wasting time!
Let's get a move on!
Atori...?
This is irritating!
Send me to Shangri-la, now!
Tobi.
I'll take them all out!
Are you listening to me?!
I will not ask you again!
Send me to Shangri-la!
Do it now!
[MIHO]
What's wrong with you, Atori?!
How come you're
talking so mean now?!
No, Atori, don't!
Listen, you!
Wanna fight me?!
I don't know why
you're doing this!
[AI]
Miho!
Kosagi!
Don't make me say it again!
Get me there!
No, it's too risky!
The chances of sending you
to Shangri-la at currentl--
Stop giving me flimsy excuses!
Just do what you're told!
Atori, what's wrong with you?!
This is impossible!
Stop!
--What's the matter with you?!
--[ISAMI] Miho!
Get out of my way!
Don't you get mad at me!
'Cause I'm the one who's
mad at you right now!
What are you saying?!
If you don't stop acting
so mean to everyone,
I will never, ever forgive you,
and I won't play
with you anymore!
We won't go to the Wizard Park
or anywhere else fun ever again!
Will you keep quiet?!
No I will not!
Damn.
Stop your noise. It's annoying.
[ATORI] Can't you think
of another way, Tobi?
Atori...
If we don't do something
about Shangri-la soon,
it's gonna swallow up the world
where these guys
are living, too.
Impossible...
It's up to me to protect
these little guys.
[YU] Hey, Karasu,
can I ask you somethin'?
[KARASU]
What is it?
Is life still hard,
even after you're a grown-up?
I think life is probably
easier when you're just a kid
and don't know anything.
You go through some tough
stuff as a kid too, y'know.
Well, okay, maybe you do.
But when you start to grow up,
the memories of your childhood
become a little blurry.
That's cool. My childhood
kinda sucks anyway.
It's not that fun,
and if I was older,
I could do whatever I want.
[KARASU]
You really think so?
Well, yeah.
Just because you're
older doesn't mean
you have the freedom
to do as you wish.
You'll be broken apart by
unimaginable pain and sorrow
that, as a simple child,
you can't even fathom.
What are you saying?
That's exactly why you
must become strong.
So that even when you encounter
overwhelming pain and grief,
you can have the strength
to overcome it.
Wait a minute... You mean
in the future, Haruka is dead?
Well, answer me!
[KOORIYAMA] Hey, is that
kinda strange-lookin' kid
still up there?
Go get her; I got a
favor I gotta ask her.
Okay!
Tobi, Mr. Kooiryama
wants to see you.
Oh? Now what does he want?
[doorbells chime]
It's been a long time.
So how've you been?
[MAYUZUMI]
Sorry for the short notice.
How has Haruka been doing?
Why are you asking me that?
You just saw her the
other day, didn't you?
Uh-- Oh, right, of course.
[ASUKA]
What's wrong?
Is it work? I thought
you were in Tokyo.
[MAYUZUMI]
Not right now.
I, uh, needed to discuss
something with you.
Will you and Haruka
come to Tokyo with me?
A little sudden,
don't you think?
I really need you there!
I'll find you an apartment!
Please, stop this! You know
I can't just pick up and go!
An experiment is going to be run
here very shortly. You should--
[ASUKA]
Is it that dangerous?
I can't tell you anymore
than I have already.
Please just do it for me.
You haven't changed one bit!
You always think you're
right about everything!
Do your experiment
somewhere else!
I was born in this town
and I'm not going to go!
You haven't changed either! You
never listen to anybody else!
I think I've heard enough!
I'm leaving!
Asuka, wait!
I'm begging you, please!
You're Haruka's mother,
aren't you?!
How about considering the
safety of your only child?!
[ASUKA]
Excuse me?!
What do you think gives
you the right to--
[ASUKA]
We're doing it again, aren't we?
It's so horrible. I suppose
old habits really die hard.
I guess I take back
what I just said.
You have changed quite a bit.
You've become a lot calmer.
So what's wrong?
I feel it's my duty to
protect the two of you.
Asuka. The next time we meet,
let's go to that park again
like we used to with Haruka.
I'll call you
again soon. I promise.
[KARASU] The Haruka of
my world became a part
of the quantum computer.
In your dimension, that will
occur in about 10 years.
Why does it happen to her?
[KARASU]
That was what Haruka desired.
[KARASU] She sacrificed herself
for the existence of La'cryma.
Haruka was chosen
in an effort to stop
the takeover from Shangri-la.
She became the wall,
which prevented erosion
from other dimensions.
She did it for the "Limes,"
the dimensional barrier
created by the quantum computer.
She became the human sacrifice
that saved La'cryma
from destruction.
I... let Haruka die.
So in the future...
[HARUKA]
That me in La'cryma...
She was smiling, right?
[KARASU]
Haruka!
So I guess the me in La'cryma
also loved you, Karasu.
That right?
She didn't do it for everyone.
She did it for you, Karasu.
[NOEIN]
That's right.
Haruka from all
dimensions will disappear.
Get away, now!
Yu!
[NOEIN]
Die, you scum!
What are you doing?!
[NOEIN]
Oh, Haruka...
[HARUKA] They have nothing
to do with this, right?!
So if I were to go with you...
[NOEIN] That's true. If it is
your wish, I will not harm them.
Ha... ruka...
[NOEIN] You and I together
will unite all dimensions,
and give birth
to the true world.
Haruka, your existence
can save everything.
Including my friends here, both?
Promise me that you'll send them
back to their own dimensions.
[NOEIN]
If that is your wish...
Don't do it... Haruka...
[NOEIN] You have made
the correct choice.
Let go of her!
Damn you! Bring her back!
Keep your promise!
Send them back, right now!
[NOEIN]
A promise indeed! So true!
But you know something, Haruka?
You will soon forget
all about them.
[NOEIN] Please realize the world
is a chain of unhappiness,
and that you are the
first link in that chain.
[AI] Do you think
Miss Uchida and the others
have a plan in the works?
I hope they came up with one.
[MIHO] Atori, Tobi hasn't
come back yet.
Just be patient.
[MIHO]
Yeah, but--
What's happening?
What was that?!
[ATORI]
Come here!
Here, grab on!
What in the hell's goin' on?!
I don't like this.
Tell me you know
what's goin' on!
What just happened?!
It's gone!
[NOEIN]
Perfect...
It can't be! My house!
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
How can you tell that
the future is miserable?
[NOEIN] So then, why don't you
return them to their world?
[ATORI] Everyone is waiting,
you're not alone.
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "To the Future."
Can you find a happy one?