[AI]
No way!
W-Why have all the houses
around us disappeared?
[ISAMI]
Impossible! Am I dreaming?!
[AI]
No, no, it's no dream.
That hurt!
[MIHO]
It's aliens!
[ISAMI, AI]
Huh?
Our alien friends have finally
invited us to their home planet!
Huh?! What if
there's no oxygen?!
What if they're from Venus?
They could be little gray men.
It sure looks like we've
been teleported somewhere...
I say we go outside!
[ATORI]
I wouldn't.
Why not?
Your assumption's correct.
Our surroundings are different.
We've all been transported
along with the house.
So then, you know where we are?
[ATORI]
Yes... It's Shangri-la.
[AI]
Shangri-la?
Ai! Miho! Isami!
[NOEIN] I bet that
deep down, you actually do
desire this happy world,
this Shangri-la.
That's why you invited
your friends here, isn't it?
You're wrong! I wanna go back!
I... I want to go back
to my dimension.
[NOEIN]
So... Then why not return them
to their original world?
Please, guys, go back
to your own world!
[NOEIN]
It won't change now.
Because you already
wished for it.
Because you saw
them in this world,
they are now established
to exist in this world.
Hang in there... Haruka...
I'll get you out of this!
[NOEIN] Aren't you glad?
They will be freed
from an unhappy future
with their arrival in this
dimension. This Shangri-la.
It won't be just them.
We shall save every future
in every dimension.
You have the ability
to do it, Haruka.
How can you tell that
the future is unhappy?
[NOEIN] I have seen the
futures of every dimension.
[NOEIN] Very well. I shall show
you their future as well.
[ATORI] Don't do it. You don't
know what could happen.
But we have to find Haruka.
And out friend Yu, too!
Do whatever you want then.
[MIHO]
Okay, we will do what we want.
[ATORI]
Miho! You're going with them?
Will you come with us, Atori?
Do I have any other choice?
You ready?
[MIYUKI] Their parents died
five years ago, didn't they?
[ASUKA]
Yes, they did.
The children were raised
by their grandmother.
[MIYUKI] Oh, those poor kids.
What are they gonna do now?
[ASUKA] I heard they'll be
taken in by distant relatives.
[MIYUKI] I'm told Isami will
be taken in by a friend
of his deceased father.
[ASUKA]
It's a shame that brothers
have to be split up like that.
Isami...
[NOEIN] Ah... the chain
of unhappiness has begun.
[HARUKA]
What do you mean?!
[NOEIN]
This is only the beginning
of their unhappy future.
[GIRL A] Did you see
the new guy? He's cute.
[GIRL B]
Dreamy!
[NOEIN]
Poor thing.
She doesn't seem
to have any friends.
Who, Miho?
[NOEIN]
And as for the others...
[GIRL C]
Hey, Ai. Ai!
[AI]
Hmm?
[GIRL C] Is it true?
What I heard was that
you made the
all-star soccer team!
[AI]
Yeah, I did.
[GIRL D] Wow! That's incredible!
Give 'em your best!
[AI]
Thanks!
[GIRL C] I know I'll be
watching every game!
[GIRL D] Make sure you
score a lot of goals!
Thanks a lot, I'll do my best!
[GIRL D] Go get 'em!
[GIRL C] For sure!
[AI]
Huh?
Isami...
Oh, disgusting.
It's those punks from North.
You should tell your friend
not to hang out with those guys.
They get into a lot of fights.
[GIRL C]
You know him?
Yeah, we were classmates
back in elementary...
[PUNK A]
Get him!
[PUNK B]
Isami, get it already!
[ISAMI]
Haha, let's go!
[NOEIN]
What do you think?
Do you still consider
this a "happy future?"
Isami...
[ASUKA]
Miyuki! Miyuki!
[MIYUKI]
Coming! Hold on a second.
It's gone! It's gone!
I don't know where it went!
Hold it! What are you
talking about, Asuka?
[ASUKA]
Just come with me!
[MIYUKI]
What's wrong?!
What is it?!
[ASUKA]
Look! It's gone!
[MIYUKI]
Gone?! What's gone?
Can't you see?!
My house is gone!
What do you mean?
How can your house go away?
That's what I'd like to know!
Oh, what's going on?!
Somebody explain it to me!
No! Haruka was in the house!
She was in the house!
What do I do? Wha--Aaah!
Just calm down, Asuka!
[ASUKA panting]
[ASUKA sobs]
Oh, Yu...
[YU groans]
[KARASU]
What now?
It looked farther
away awhile ago,
so I think we must
be getting closer.
[KARASU]
Huh?
You know, the mountain there
that looks like a castle.
[KARASU]
What are you talking about?
It's still a long way off.
What the heck are you
looking at, Karasu?
It's right over there,
can't you see it?
So to you, it doesn't look
that far away from here.
You mean you can't see that?
I understand. Maybe it's because
this space-time is de-coherent.
[YU]
What?
[KARASU] It's the same as when
you split into two in La'cryma.
This place is also indistinct
without an
established existence.
So everything around
me is an illusion?
[KARASU]
Not really.
Your strong desire
to save Haruka
has established this
indistinct space.
Then if I... were to think
about where she could be...
The path will begin
to show itself.
[KARASU]
Get down!
[MIHO sobbing]
[PUNK A]
Hey, that's a bit harsh, Isami.
We're workin'
hard too, ya know.
[PUNK B]
Yeah, lighten up, man.
[ISAMI]
Whatever. You guys suck.
[PUNK A]
Come on, man.
[PUNK B]
Isami, just listen to me.
The thing is, my girl said--
[AI]
Isami?
[ISAMI]
Huh?
How's it goin'?
It's been awhile...
[ISAMI]
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, this chick
a friend of yours?
[ISAMI]
So, what's goin' on?
[AI] Nothing, really.
I'm just on my way home
from afterschool practice.
Oh. I guess you're still doin'
all that soccer horsecrap?
[AI]
Yeah. And what are you doing?
Now that's none
of your business.
Do you even have a clue
what you're doing?!
You know, this tough act
doesn't really suit you!
[ISAMI]
Psh. Don't lecture me.
Why don't you just
get out of my life?
No, I won't!
Get the hell outta here!
[AI]
Ah...
You never really
got it, did you?!
Just leave me alone!
[ISAMI]
Go away!
[PUNK C]
Hey there. I hear you guys
haven't been on your
best behavior lately.
So then. Let's talk,
come to an agreement.
[ISAMI]
Get up!
[PUNK A] Where do you
think you're going?!
[PUNK A] Take a good
look at your opponent
before you pick a fight!
[ISAMI]
Alright!
Let's get outta here.
[PUNK B]
What are you talkin' about?
We got a reputation, man!
We gotta finish it!
Really?
You really wanna pull
a knife on me?
You want a piece of me, huh?!
Go ahead, do it!
What is this, all for show?!
I ain't scared of you, man!
You want me to kick your ass a
little more, is that it?! Huh?!
No problem! I can do that! Easy!
Knock it off.
That's fine by me! Let's go,
you bastard! Let's get it on!
[ISAMI]
I said knock it off!
Shit...
[PUNK C]
Let's get outta here!
[PUNK D]
This is bad...
Real bad!
[HARUKA]
Isami...
[NOEIN] The poor thing... He's
been abandoned by his "friends."
Impossible...
[UCHIDA] There are 5
laboratory ships in all.
This mountain is where they
will be aligned in a circle
and launch elementary particles.
The 5 ships will be used
to accelerate the particles,
forcing the quantum potential
to bend along the circle.
They will launch three
particles: Alpha, Beta, Gamma.
The particles will be
accelerated in the Magic Circle
until they achieve light speed.
When every particle
is at the speed of light,
the dimension is
at the critical point
which will produce
the Theta particles.
I see. There are
a few differences
from our history, but not many.
[UCHIDA]
In what way?
[TOBI]
I think perhaps your history
is happening five years faster.
Do you think that's due
to violation of causation
rather than our world being just
bein' an approximate dimension?
[TOBI]
Probably.
Uh, excuse me.
I think that's enough
of the complicated crap, okay?
Besides, all we really need to
do is destroy this thing, right?
[SHINOHARA]
A 1985 Romanée-Conte.
It's flavor is described
as "mystifying."
It's known as the greatest
beverage created by man.
How about it, Mayuzumi?
Wouldn't you agree
it's a suitable wine
for this historic event?
Shinohara. I'll ask once again.
Stop the experiment.
[SHINOHARA] Come on, now,
Doctor. Don't get so worked-up.
Thanks to you
finding this place,
the Magic Circle looks
like it'll work.
[UCHIDA]
Thank you.
[TOBI]
You alright?
[UCHIDA]
You okay there?
[KOORIYAMA]
I'm not so thrilled about
floatin' around in the air.
But now that my feet are back on
solid ground, I guess I'm okay.
Listen to me--
[SHINOHARA]
It's fine! It's a path mankind
is bound to take someday anyway.
Drink up.
Hey, if I don't do it,
someone else will.
[SHINOHARA]
The thing about mankind is,
we always wanna get ahead.
We're not happy
with the status quo.
We remember the
guys who got ahead
with admiration and jealousy.
And now, as long as mankind
exists in the Universe,
I will be remembered
as a forward-thinker
who created a new era.
Um, wow!
[YU] That's weird... It seems
like it's farther away now.
[KARASU]
It's your fear.
The fear that you
have inside you
keeps pushing
Haruka further away.
It's me?
To save her, don't run away.
Show strength. Face up to it.
I'll do that, Karasu.
[GIRL C] I heard this guy
was in a knife fight
and got blinded in one eye.
[GIRL D] No way!
Was it those guys we saw?!
[GIRL C] Yeah! I think it was
the one that Ai said she knew.
[GIRL D]
Really?!
Hey there, Ai!
It's true? Isami got hurt?!
[GIRL D]
Wait!
[AI groans]
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine...
[AI groans]
[ambulance siren blaring]
[knocking]
[MIHO'S MOM] Miho! Miho...
stop hiding from the world
and come out now!
You've been shut in
there for two weeks.
Can you hear me? Miho!
[AI]
Um, Doctor?
I have a soccer game
a few days from now.
Will I be ready by then?
[DOCTOR] I need you to
listen to me and remain calm.
What?
[DOCTOR] I'm saying that
you have to give up soccer.
The fact is, if we don't
amputate your left leg
within the next three months,
you may lose your life.
[MIHO'S MOM] Miho...
Please come out... Please?
Miho?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
[THERAPIST] Clearly, it's a
depersonalization disorder.
I suspect that it stems from
her desire to deny reality
due to extreme stress.
[HARUKA]
Stop it! No! No more!
I hate this future!
[NOEIN]
I told you.
The future contains
nothing but unhappiness.
But you wanted to see the
so-called "possibilities"
that the future had to offer.
I'll never believe it!
This isn't the future!
[NOEIN] Then would you like
to see more of the future?
[HARUKA]
No!
[NOEIN] You are the only one
who can cut away this future.
With your Dragon Torque power,
you can change every unhappy
future into Shangri-la.
Is that true...?
[NOEIN] That's right.
And once you do that,
there will never be an unhappy
future for all eternity.
What is it?
Haruka!
Haruka?
She said "Help everyone...
Help them all."
[YU]
Isami.
[ISAMI]
Huh?
What do you think you're doing?
[ISAMI]
Yu?
Stop it, you're not like this.
What are you doin' here, man?
When did you get
back from Tokyo?
Listen to me, Isami. Find Ai.
You are the only one who
can save her life now.
[ISAMI]
Me?
Of course.
Who else is gonna do it?
Listen--!
[ATORI]
Miho.
I've been looking for you.
So this is where
you wandered off to.
[MIHO]
Who... Who are you?
[ATORI] Let's go home.
Back to where your friends are.
[MIHO]
No...
This is not the place
you belong. You know that.
[ISAMI]
Ai!
[AI]
Isami?
What are you standing
over there for?
It's dangerous!
Come over here!
[AI]
What did you come here for?
Did you come here to
laugh at me? Is that it?
Because I won't be able
to play soccer anymore?
Hell, I can barely walk...
[ISAMI]
You idiot! What's one leg?!
Look at me! I lost an eye!
It doesn't matter, I'm done...
[ISAMI]
No! You're not done!
[ISAMI] Even if you don't have
your legs, if you wanna run,
I'll run with you on my back!
We can play soccer that way!
[ISAMI]
So please...
Please don't do this, okay?
[ISAMI]
Come here.
Oh, Isami...
[ATORI]
They're all waiting.
They are?
[ATORI]
You are not alone.
[MIHO]
I'm not?
[ATORI]
Come on, let's go.
It's okay. Everyone's safe now.
That's good.
Let's go.
This time, I'll find Haruka.
I swear it.
Isami, we--
Yes, Ai?
I was having a dream.
Me too.
Atori?
[ATORI]
It was no dream.
That was just one of
many future dimensions
that were consumed
by Shangri-la.
[MIHO] Wait a minute,
that was out future?
[ATORI]
One possible future.
[HARUKA]
They're back! They're all back!
The future's not set in stone!
Even if we encounter
unhappiness in the future,
we will never give up!
[NOEIN cackling]
[NOEIN] But one of you
couldn't endure the misfortune.
Do you know who it was?
It was your friend, Yu.
His future self.
And you already
realized that, didn't you?
[NOEIN]
I am the Yu of this dimension.
Haruka... My dear...
You left me behind
when you died...
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[NOEIN] All dimensions
will unite and disappear.
[KARASU] Yu, do not fear.
Think only of Haruka.
[YU] I don't understand it,
but I have to save Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "The End."
Is everyone going to disappear?