[HARUKA growls]
[WOMAN]
Do you know where this is?
Over there? I see it.
Thank you for help. Bye.
[HARUKA]
Dad!
Huh? Hey! Haruka!
Princess, hi!
Uh, what's the problem, honey?
Well, I'm too old for
all that kid's stuff now.
Really? Aww...
[HARUKA] Now, this is
a lot more grown-up.
Yes, you're all grown up.
Who did I see you
just talking to, Dad?
What do you mean?
That woman!
Oh, you saw that, huh?
Well, I guess your old dad's
still got it, right?
Hmph! I don't think I like
the way she was looking at you!
[MAYUZUMI]
Oh yeah?
[HARUKA]
Yeah! This is our time together!
[BOTH laugh]
[MAYUZUMI] You're sure you
don't mind coming here?
[HARUKA]
Of course not. I like it.
[MAYUZUMI]
I'll be honest with you.
I'm kinda relieved that my
princess still likes coming
to amusement parks.
Hey, Dad! Remember that?
Huh?
Those rides over there!
Remember when I was
still in Tokyo, and we all
used to go to Grandma's
house for summer break?
[MAYUZUMI] That was a long time
ago. You still remember that?
Yeah, back when
Grandma was still alive,
before Mom and I
moved in the house.
That was a while ago.
[HARUKA] We all came here
together. It was so much fun.
[MAYUZUMI]
Hmm...
Are you still upset
that I went away?
No, not anymore.
I was just... you know.
Thinking about all the
fun times we had together.
Hey, Dad?
[MAYUZUMI]
Yeah, Princess?
Do you think this place
will still be here
when I get to be your age?
Huh? Sure it will.
Hey, listen, you're not still
seeing those ghosts
again are you?
Hm? Ghosts?
When you were little, you cried
and said you saw
ghosts all the time.
Oh, yeah, that. Turns out
they weren't really ghosts.
What?!
[phone rings]
Huh?
Hmm.
Whaddaya want?
[SHINOHARA] Hey, Doc Mayuzumi!
You hidin' from me?
Where ya been?
You should really tell me
when you change your
cell phone number.
I thought I told you we
needed to have a little talk.
You're with your
daughter now, aren't you?
You haven't seen her in a while,
right? Enjoy it while you can.
You never can tell when a
horrible accident can happen.
Twelve-year old girls get
hit by cars every day.
I mean, you're a part-time dad.
You can't watch over
her all the time!
[SHINOHARA chuckles]
[MAYUZUMI]
All right, when should we meet?
Where?
[MAYUZUMI]
Alright, in two hours, then.
I'm sorry, honey,
but I have to go.
Work, huh?
Yeah. I have to go back
to the hotel right away.
[HARUKA] Heh, that's all right.
Go get all your work done!
[MAYUZUMI]
Huh?
[HARUKA]
I don't mind.
Because next time, I'm going
to come see you in Tokyo!
What? You are?
It's just Tokyo;
I can get there myself.
Then I'll let you
really spoil me.
[MAYUZUMI]
Hey, don't push so hard.
I'm not that young any more.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, yeah. Move it!
[BOTH grunt]
[ISAMI laughs]
[YU laughs]
[AI] So what did your
dad get you this time?
[HARUKA] Nothing.
He got called back to work.
He had to take off right away.
What?! But your dad came
all this way to see you!
I know. It stinks.
Yeah, it does.
Next time you see him,
you gotta make him
totally spoil you rotten
to make up for this time!
Absolutely!
Haruka... Tobi's gone.
You know where she might be?
She's gone?
Maybe she just went for a walk.
[ATORI]
Karasu's gone too.
[MIHO]
Atori, don't look so sad.
Here, have some of these.
Hey, thank you so much.
Hey, you big goof ball!
You put them in your mouth!
I think Miho... really has
a big crush on Atori.
[TOBI] I'm afraid I'm
getting a negative reading.
A dimensional strain is
germinating from this point.
[TOBI]
Karasu?
What is it, Tobi?
Is there anything bothering you?
No.
Do you remember
when we were kids?
When we just believed that time
moved from past to future.
[TOBI]
Yeah, that's right.
We really didn't know
any better back then.
[KARASU] But the concept of
time isn't just a measurement
created by man.
We learned that it's
really a fluctuating value
which is linked with space.
That is correct.
[KARASU] When mankind figured
out that time and space
were always changing
without stability,
perhaps we lost sight of
the meaning of existence.
Maybe we are all... illusions.
Myself, Haruka...
This dimension... La'cryma...
You're wrong about that.
Huh?
We both know that our existence
is actually established
by observation.
You're the one who found Haruka,
and that is why
she truly exists.
And then, Haruka found
you here as well...
And that is why you truly exist.
[KOORIYAMA]
Is there a reason
we're driving around
this mountain?
I'm tryin' to attach a numerical
value to the quantum potential.
And do you think that'll finally
help to persuade those guys?
I don't think it'll work
with the committee... But...
I'm sure someone like
Dr. Mayuzumi will understand.
[KOORIYAMA] Do we have any
idea where this guy is yet?
No, but I'm sure he'll
visit Haruka sometime soon.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's them.
[UCHIDA] Huh? What do
you think you're doin'?
Just stay in the car, okay?
Hey, I'm not stayin' in here!
[KOORIYAMA]
Hey, you!
[KARASU] Huh?
[TOBI] Huh?
[KOORIYAMA] You mind tellin' me
what you're doin' over there?
[TOBI]
Karasu!
Y'see, I'm a cop, and I'd like
to ask ya a few questions.
[UCHIDA]
Kooriyama!
Come on now, buddy, I know ya
understand what I'm sayin',
don'tcha? Get over here, now!
Hmph!
[KOORIYAMA] I told ya
to get your ass over here!
Hold it there!
[UCHIDA gasps]
I see, some kind
of magician, are ya?!
Huh?
[KOORIYAMA]
Why you wearing a heavy cape
when it's this
frickin' hot, huh?!
Who in the hell are you anyway?
It doesn't matter. You wouldn't
understand the answer.
Just turn around and walk away.
[KOORIYAMA] I don't think so,
pal. You're gonna start talkin',
and you're gonna
tell me what I wanna hear
and I better like the answers!
Now, who the hell are you
and what the hell
are you doin' here?
In ten years...
Huh?!
When ten years have
passed in this dimension,
you might be able to
comprehend my existence.
I think I've heard enough.
How 'bout you and I have
a nice, long conversation...
...in a rubber room
somewhere, huh?!
Just wait a minute!
Tell me, are you a
transported existence
from a time-space
several years ahead?
Where the solution of relativity
between quantum mechanicals
and space-time has
been identified?!
[TOBI] I'm not sure
Karasu understands that.
But you're definitely
on the right track.
You're pretty smart, lady.
You might actually comprehend
how we've come to
exist in your world.
Who the hell are you?
Are you with him?
[YU]
Hey, Isami?
[ISAMI]
Yeah?
[YU]
Can I ask you something?
[ISAMI]
Sure.
It's about Haruka.
I think she's got these
strange powers or something.
Where'd that come from?
Nah, she doesn't. You're
startin' to sound like Miho.
[YU]
I know... But why does Karasu
keep tellin' me to protect her?
We are men, after all.
It's our job to keep women safe.
Yeah... Uh...
Do you, you know, like anyone?
Huh? Yeah, of course I do!
I wouldn't be a stud if
I didn't like the ladies!
So, anyone in particular?
[ISAMI]
Yeah, but you can't tell anyone.
What?! Ms. Yukie?!
[ISAMI] Shut up, you idiot!
You're impossible!
Keep your voice down!
Everyone knows.
It's not a secret.
Wha--?! Impossible!
How'd they know that?!
Just forget it. I'm sorry
I even asked you about it.
What is that supposed
to mean?! I really like her!
Yeah, yeah...
What's this? Some more magic?
This area is
definitely suspicious.
[UCHIDA] Is there a
quantum potential here?
[TOBI]
Most likely.
It's coming from in there.
I'm getting a reading
from that area.
Let's go.
Hey, where are you going?
Let's go!
Hey, wait!
Oh, boy...
[AI] What?! No,
I've sprung a leak again!
And I'm all out of wrenches!
[MIHO giggles]
Aw, crap! Yeah, take that!
Don't think so!
It'll take more than that trick
to disrupt my water supply!
Aw, no, she got my pipe again!
[HARUKA]
You're good at this, Miho!
[MIHO]
Nobody can defeat me!
[AI]
It's a trap!
[HARUKA]
Ai, you're terrible.
[AI groans]
[ATORI gasps]
[MIHO]
Huh? Hey, what's the matter?
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[AI]
Ah?
[ATORI]
It's them.
[MIHO]
Who?
[UCHIDA] I have a confirmed
reading over here.
But, it isn't a very strong one.
That's it, alright. It's making
a small critical reaction.
[KOORIYAMA]
Hey, what's over there?
[TOBI]
Karasu, come here.
[KOORIYAMA]
Huh?!
[KARASU]
Is this it?
[TOBI]
There's an irregular fluctuation
germinating from in there.
What do you see?
Straight ahead.
Yeah.
What? I can't see anything.
Only we can.
It's at the
critical stage, all right!
At the critical stage?!
What's that?!
[KARASU gasps]
Where the hell
did that come from?
It must be the
dimensional contact point.
[KOORIYAMA]
Huh?
Uroboros...
An Uroboros...
Hey, what're you doin'?!
Be careful!
No, don't do that!
It passed right through!
Tobi, is this...?
You are looking at an
undefined existence.
Let me put this in terms
you can understand.
It's an overlapped state.
It's a quantum existence only.
Perfect! More techno-babble
that I don't understand!
Let me see now...
So even when I see it,
it doesn't really exist?!
Or am I just going insane?
Well, how about it?!
[MIHO]
Bye!
[HARUKA] Atori, thanks
for walking them home.
--[ATORI] I'll see you.
--[AI] See ya!
[MIHO]
See you tomorrow!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[MIHO]
What're you doing, Haruka?
Uh, wha--?
It's your turn, put a card down!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[AI]
She's totally spacing out again!
[KARASU grunts]
[KOORIYAMA]
Hey, what's wrong?
[UCHIDA]
Tobi?
This oscillation...
It's Shangri-la!
[UCHIDA]
What's Shangri-la?
[KARASU] It's him!
The mask of Shangri-la!
The mask...?
Oh no, Haruka! She's in danger!
[KARASU yells]
[AI] Aww, there's no more
water works cards.
Haruka, you gotta stop her!
Huh? What's that?
[MIHO] Give it up! My victory
is still guaranteed!
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
What's happening?!
Get out!
[HARUKA]
Huh...?
Karasu!
Huh?
Come here, Haruka.
[HARUKA gasps]
Just get behind me!
Karasu?
Come here, right now.
Don't be afraid.
No way.
You aren't Karasu.
Who are you?
Come to me, Haruka!
Huh?
It's that mask!
[KARASU gasps]
[MASK] Haruka, come with
me to Shangri-la!
[KARASU]
Be careful!
Haruka, here!
Huh? What is it, dude?
Haruka!
Huh?
She's been... kidnapped!
[voices echoing]
[HARUKA]
Huh?
What's this?
[MASK] This place is called
the dimensional ravine.
Watch yourself!
Here, get behind me, Haruka!
I'm scared...
Just stay close!
[MASK]
Haruka.
Come here.
Come to me.
The masked man.
[NOEIN] I am Noein.
The one who understands
all there is to know.
Now, come with me!
Come with me to Shangri-la!
Shangri-la?!
[NOEIN]
Yes, the ideal dimension.
I will not go with you!
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
Karasu?
What is this place?
[NOEIN]
This is Shangri-la.
There is no war
or suffering here.
It is a world veiled in silence.
This world is one of perfection.
Right now, all worlds
are trying to merge
with this ideal dimension.
[HARUKA]
Merge?
[NOEIN]
That is correct, Haruka.
Dimensions where you exist.
Even dimensions
where you don't exist.
All the different worlds
were branching off
into a disorderly mess.
Into chaos.
With infinite dimensions came
equally infinite disasters.
[NOEIN] And that is why I forced
the dimensions to conjoin...
...into La'cryma and Shangri-la.
[NOEIN]
Which of them will you choose?
It's my choice?
I have to choose?
[HARUKA gasps]
[KARASU]
Haruka!
Give me your hand!
Karasu! Here!
[KARASU]
Stay back!
[HARUKA]
Karasu!
[KARASU growls]
[NOEIN]
You fool!
[KARASU]
Be gone!
[KARASU gasps]
[HARUKA screams]
[KARASU]
Haruka...!
Why, Haruka? Why?!
Karasu...
[NOEIN]
You can forget about him.
[NOEIN] He is merely
an illusion to you.
No! He is not an illusion!
My protector is right here.
[NOEIN]
What is this?!
[NOEIN gasps]
[HARUKA]
You killed Fukuro, didn't you?
I will never believe you!
[NOEIN]
The Uroboros!
[ISAMI] Come on, dude,
what's the rush anyway?
What's up, man?
Karasu...
Where is she?
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[YU] Where is she?!
What happened to Haruka?!
[HARUKA] I get the feeling
it's slightly different.
[NOEIN laughs]
[NOEIN]
Do you want to know?
[HARUKA]
Next episode, "Repeat."
Will I be able
to meet you again?