[distant clanking, ringing]
[cat meows]
Uh...
[clanking, ringing]
Huh?
[phone ringing]
[static]
Hello, who's this?
Huh?
[squealing, static]
[HARUKA]
Hello? Hello, can you hear me?
[squealing, static]
[HARUKA]
Hello?
[distorted voice]
[MAYUZUMI]
This is Mauzumi.
[HARUKA gasps]
Hello, Dad.
[MAYUZUMI]
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
Huh?
Huh...?
What was that?
Ah. Huh?
[cat meows]
The old phone
beneath the stairs?
[HARUKA]
Mh-mm.
[ASUKA]
But that's not possible.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, I know that.
That telephone doesn't
even work anymore.
No one's even used that phone
since before Grandma was born.
What? It hasn't been
used for that long?
The last time it was used
was when your great
grandfather was alive.
[HARUKA] I really don't
think I was dreaming.
[ASUKA]
I guess it could happen.
[HARUKA]
Huh?!
Actually, I do remember
that phone ringing once
when I was a kid.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, right, Mom.
[ASUKA]
No, I'm serious.
Was I in high school, or was
I even younger than that?
[phone ringing]
[ASUKA] I just figured
I was half asleep.
I mean, there is no way that
an unconnected phone can ring.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, that's true.
Huh...
Did you do that?
I drew it a long time ago,
when I was in college.
It's really
pretty bad, isn't it?
Why are you throwing it out?
It's silly to hang onto all
these pictures, isn't it?
No, it's not. I'll keep 'em.
Mm. All right, then.
They're yours.
[HARUKA]
Thanks!
Hey, these other ones
are pretty cute also Mom.
Look at this! It's so adorable!
[ASUKA]
Okay, enough of that.
We have a lot
of cleaning to do.
Miss Yukie will be here soon.
Sorry about the short notice,
but these enviromentalists
have nowhere else to stay.
[ASUKA] Oh, that's okay.
Don't worry about it.
We have an extra room.
[YUKIE] I really can't
thank you enough.
[ASUKA]
Oh, it's nothing.
So this is a
non-profit organization?
Yes, we're studying the
migration of local birds.
It's really a great place, Tobi.
I can even see the ocean.
Yes, I know.
How about we go for a walk
once I'm finished here?
That sounds like fun.
Hello there, everyone.
[YUKIE]
Didn't take you guys long.
Oh, Miss Yukie, you're here.
[MIHO laughs]
Wow! This is great!
It's so bright
and cheery in here!
It was such a waste
to use it as a storage room.
You agree, don't you, Atori?
Okay.
[ISAMI] This is definitely
the right house.
They wouldn't all fit
at Miss Yukie's place.
[YUKIE] And excuse me for
having a cramped apartment.
[ISAMI]
I didn't mean it that way.
So he decided not to come here?
Do you mean Karasu?
I think he just
stepped out for a minute.
I don't understand why
he couldn't just stay
here with all of you.
Out of the question.
I think having him here
would cause suspicion.
He's too intense looking
to pose as an enviromentalist.
Totally, you're right.
I mean, he always has this
scary look on his face.
Crap!
[KARASU] Will this be a
sufficient place for everyone?
Yes, probably.
Although, it'll take
a little while to set up.
Is it okay for you
to be up and around?
Mh-mm.
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Hey, I brought some stuff.
You know, I could
use a little help here.
Karasu, where have you been?
You just got better,
so you shouldn't go
outside too much yet.
[YU]
Uh, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Can I have some tea?
Yeah, make sure you
pass it around to everyone.
Huh? You mean me?
[HARUKA] Yeah, make sure
everyone gets some.
Fine. Whatever.
[HARUKA]
We have snacks too.
[AI]
C'mon, Isami. Help out already.
[ISAMI]
Yeah, yeah, all right.
[YUKIE]
Tobi, is that good enough?
[TOBI] Well, this laptop
is a real antique,
but I'll try to compensate
by re-programming it.
That happens
to be the fastest,
most up-to-date
model made, you know.
[YU]
Are you sure about this?
Sure about what?
Come on, you know
what I'm saying.
[ISAMI, AI yelp]
[AI]
Whoa, they're floating.
[ISAMI]
That's impossible.
[YUKIE]
Is this some kind of magic?
[MIHO]
Move over, David Copperfield.
Okay, I'm finally in.
[AI]
Wow, is that beautiful.
[ISAMI]
Even more impossible.
Huh?
What is Tobi doing with that?
Finding something for me.
Well then, how come
you're not helping her?
Because Tobi's
a lot better at it.
Oh, I see.
[ISAMI]
Hmm?
Where ya headed, dude?
[YU]
Bathroom.
Huh?
[HARUKA]
Hey. Is something wrong?
You've been acting
kinda weird all day.
[YU]
Let's go to Tokyo.
What?
[YU] I don't think we should
be anywhere near those guys.
Do you really wanna get
dragged into more weird stuff?
Well, I don't think running
away is gonna help anything.
Hey, that's so not true!
If we got to Tokyo,
then we can find your father,
and we can get him to help us.
Hey, yeah, that's right.
My dad's coming over
to visit this Saturday.
[YU]
Huh?
He usually tries to make it
in every three months.
Well, that'll be a nice
time for ya. Have fun.
Would you stop?
I can't go anywhere.
If I really am the source of
all this, then running away
and hiding isn't going
to change anything.
So I'll just stay
here with Karasu.
I just don't think you should
be so trusting of this guy.
Ah! How come you're always
talking about Karasu
in that way?
Just forget it,
but don't come crying to me
when things get freaky again.
[HARUKA] Wait a minute.
What are you so pissed about?
[YU]
I'm not pissed!
[HARUKA]
Uh, yeah you are.
[YU]
Am not!
[HARUKA]
Yes, you are too!
I am not mad! Just let it go!
[HARUKA gasps]
Wow, I wonder why he's so mad.
Huh?
[phone ringing]
Hello? Who's this?
[MAYUZUMI]
This is Mayuzumi.
Huh?! Is that you, Dad?
[MAYUZUMI]
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
[HARUKA]
Where is this?
Tokyo?
[HARUKA]
Mom?
[phone ringing]
[HARUKA]
This room...
This is the house I was born in.
Huh?
Wha... What are you doin' here?
[KARASU]
We need to talk.
Come on.
How the hell am I supposed
to get up there?
Great! That's just fine!
[YUKIE]
Haruka!
I have to get going soon!
Where are you anyway?
Oh hey, were you just leaving?
Oh, hi. I'll come check in
on them tomorrow.
Do you know where
Haruka went off to?
Not really.
She may have gone to the store
to pick up a few things.
[phone ringing]
[MAYUZUMI]
Hello? This is Mayuzumi.
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Did you say "Dad"?
I think that you have
the wrong number.
That's my dad.
[ASUKA]
You are angry, aren't you?
Just tell me that
you're angry! Ugh!
We'll talk about it later.
I have to go. Bye.
[ASUKA]
What's wrong?
Why won't you talk to me?
[ASUKA sobing]
Please don't cry, Mother.
Why can't I ever just
tell her what I'm feeling?
Dammit!
Dad, don't go! Please.
[HARUKA]
That's me when I was eight.
Now I remember.
Dad didn't come home that night,
and Mom and Dad
got divorced soon after.
No.
[phone ringing]
[phones ringing]
[HARUKA gasps]
[MAYUZUMI]
This is Mayuzumi.
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
[HARUKA]
No! Not again!
It's that same moment in time.
[MIHO]
Ooh! This is amazing witchcraft.
I wonder where Karasu
has disappeared to.
[ATORI]
He's over there.
Huh?
See him? Right there.
[AI]
What's he doing up there?
[MIHO] Hey, look at that!
He's climbing the tree.
Amazing. That's not
something you see everyday.
I'm going to go outside.
[MIHO]
Hey, wait for me, Atori.
[ISAMI]
I guess we should all just go.
[AI]
Yeah, that sounds good to me.
Okay, I'm here. What d'you want?
It's sad that climbing
a tree takes such effort.
[YU]
Just tell me what you want!
Haruka will be exposed
to more and more danger.
Yeah, because you're here.
I will protect her
as long as I am alive.
Uh...
However, if the day comes
that I cannot protect her,
then you must do it.
What are you talking about?
I can't do any of the
things that you can do.
Then you must become stronger.
Oh... Yeah, right.
[YU gasps]
[KARASU] Listen kid;
you must protect Haruka.
Well, why don't you
just keep doing it?
Enough of this!
Haruka likes you better
anyway, doesn't she?
[KARASU gasps]
You're jealous.
That's what it is, isn't it?
What? What are
you talking about?
[KARASU]
Do you like her?
Huh? What do you mean,
"Do I like her?"
No, not really.
I don't think so.
[YU] When I first met her,
she just kinda bugged me.
But...
[YOUNG HARUKA gasps]
[YU]
But she had such a cute smile.
I... guess I like her.
So that was when it started.
[KARASU]
You'll protect her.
[YU]
Hmm?
[KARASU]
Be strong.
I like Haruka...
[phone ringing]
[HARUKA gasps]
[MAYUZUMI]
This is Mayuzumi.
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
[ASUKA]
You are angry, aren't you?
Just tell me that you're angry!
We'll talk about it later.
I have to go. Bye.
Dad, don't go!
[phone ringing]
Huh?!
[HARUKA]
I'm back here again?
[MAYUZUMI]
This is Mayuzumi.
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
[ASUKA]
You are angry, aren't you?
Tell me that you're angry! Ugh!
Dad! Wait!
Ugh! Is there anything
I can say to make you happy?!
This is different.
I wish I had an answer for you.
We'll talk about it later.
I have to go. Bye.
Dad, don't go!
You can't just leave us!
Huh?
[phone ringing]
Hello? This is Mayuzumi.
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
You're angry, aren't you?
You're angry, aren't you?!
Say it!
Ugh! Is there anything
I can say to make you happy?!
I wish I had an answer for you.
You'll never be satisfied
with what you have.
I gave up all of my dreams so
that you and I could be married!
I never asked you
to do that for me!
Wait a sec...
None of this is right.
So I suppose all of this
is my fault,
is that what
you're trying to say?
Will you just give me
a break already?
It's all my fault, isn't it?
[ASUKA] You're always
trying to blame m--
[MAYUZUMI]
Enough!
No, stop it! That's not right!
[TIME DRIFTER] Which past
do you want to see, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
It's you.
As you wander through
the countless dimensions,
which exist in the past,
ask yourself: what is it exactly
that you are searching for?
No matter where, or how much,
you exaimine your past,
it will never change.
But that's not true.
[MAYUZUMI]
We'll talk about it later.
I have to go. Bye.
[ASUKA] You don't even
wanna talk to me anymore.
[phone ringing]
[MAYUZUMI]
This is Mayuzumi.
Did you say "Dad"?
I think you have
the wrong number.
[click]
[HARUKA gasps]
[ASUKA sobbing] Augh!
I wish I had never met you!
Mom, don't say that.
Believe me! If I could
do it over again,
I would not have you in my life!
[HARUKA] I don't understand
what's going on.
This is your past.
It will never alter.
And yet, you continue
to search in spite of this?
How long do you plan
to keep searching?
Until they stop fighting
and patch things up.
[TIME DRIFTER]
You don't understand.
That past is not one that
is linked to your dimension.
Huh? Why not?
[TIME DRIFTER]
Because this is no more
than an approximate dimension.
[ASUKA sobing]
I wish I wasn't so clumsy.
If I hadn't tripped that day,
we would have never met.
That one day...
[COLLEAGUE] Take care of
tomorrow's report, will ya?
[MAYUZUMI] No problem, but
you're buying lunch, all right?
[COLLEAGUE] Yeah, whatever.
Okay, it's on me.
See you later.
[MAYUZUMI]
Later.
[HARUKA]
Dad?
Uh. Huh?
[MAYUZUMI]
Wow! These are great!
Huh? You think so?
Yeah, really nice.
Hey, this is especially cute.
[ASUKA]
Oh, thanks.
[MAYUZUMI]
Did you draw these?
Um, yes, I did.
[MAYUZUMI] Do you mind
if I look through them?
[ASUKA]
Go ahead. I guess it's okay.
Your use of color
is really great.
[ASUKA]
Oh, thanks.
[MAYUZUMI] I think
I like this one the best.
Cute puppy.
Well, actually, that's a cat.
[MAYUZUMI laughs]
Of course, I knew it was a cat.
I'm just messin' with ya.
Oh... Heh...
[MAYUZUMI]
This one's incredible.
The rendering style is great.
Do you study art?
My major is traditional
Japanese art.
What about you?
I'm studying quantum data
processing engineering.
Wow! That sounds like an
incredibly difficult major.
You don't really look like
the geeky engineer type.
Why, thank you, but that's
actually what I am.
Hey! This one's
really nice as well.
A tasmanian devil!
Hmph. Nice try.
It's a raccoon.
Ha! I'm playin' with ya.
You are?
[BOTH laugh]
[TIME DRIFTER]
I'm sure you can find a past
where they never met
in some other dimension.
Just know, that
doing so would have
no meaning for you in any way.
[TIME DRIFTER]
Because they will never lead
to the dimension in which
you actually exist.
You're saying I can't
change the past?
[TIME DRIFTER]
Mm-hm.
I think that's really okay.
They really got along
great back then.
[TOBI] This dimension
is getting more unstable
than I predicted.
This disturbance...
I've felt this before.
I know. It's exactly like it was
before Shangri-la began
its intervention on La'cryma.
[ATORI] We're all going out
for another walk tomorrow.
[TOBI] That sounds like
a great idea, Atori.
I just can't wait.
[MAYUZUMI]
What's wrong Haruka? What is it?
You don't usually call
this late at night.
Now don't tell me you're
planning to cancel our date?
No way, Dad.
I just felt like
talking to you. That's all.
Can I ask you something?
Do you think you might
still be in love with Mom?
[MAYUZUMI]
Where did that come from?
Just tell me.
I promise I won't tell
Mom what your answer is.
[MAYUZUMI]
I still love her.
[HARUKA]
Really? You do?
[MAYUZUMI]
But I don't think your mother
will ever forgive me.
Can I ask her that?
[MAYUZUMI] No. You promised
you wouldn't tell.
[HARUKA]
I'm sorry.
[MAYUZUMI]
Oh, I almost forgot.
Is there anywhere
special you'd like to go
when we get together?
[HARUKA]
I'd like to go for a boat ride.
[MAYUZUMI] Ha ha.
That sightseeing boat again?
We did that the last time.
[HARUKA] Oh, right.
Then, the ropeway!
[MAYUZUMI] All right, if that's
what you wanna do, sweetie.
[HARUKA]
Hmm... I'm thirsty.
[phone ringing]
Huh?
Yes? Hello? Who is this?
[FEMALE VOICE]
Hello? Hello?
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[FEMALE VOICE]
This phone shouldn't be working!
It isn't hooked up!
That sounds like Mom!
[ASUKA]
Can you hear me? Are you there?
So it was me after all.
Hey, Mom!
It's me, Haruka!
[ASUKA] Huh? Who is it?
Who's there?
[static]
[FEMALE VOICE 2]
Hello? Can you hear me?
I'm you from another dimension.
Can you hear me?
[HARUKA gasps]
[OLDER HARUKA]
How am I?
Please, don't say
anything and just listen.
When my dearest
Yu is feeling sad,
please make him feel better.
That was something
I couldn't do.
[static]
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[MAYUZUMI] Haruka, have you
started seeing ghosts again?
[HARUKA] You're wrong.
Karasu is not an illusion!
[KOORIYAMA] I'd like to hear
about it in more detail.
[HARUKA]
Next episode, "Shangri-la."
Can you see the other world?