[ISAMI]
Who's that?
[YU]
Where is she?
Tell me where
Haruka is right now!
Answer me! Tell me
what happened to her!
Where'd she go?
Hey, take it easy, man!
[YU]
She got left behind, didn't she?
[KOORIYAMA]
They... disappeared.
Okay. What the hell's
goin' on here?
The erosion of Shangri-la
is getting worse by the minute.
If this continues,
a violation of causation
could occur in this
dimension as well.
[UCHIDA]
Huh?
Actually, it may have
started already.
A violation of causation...
Say it in English, please!
So us simple humans
can understand it, too.
[UCHIDA] It means cause and
effect become reversed.
Right. And that's
a big deal because...?
The past will become
influenced by the future.
[KOORIYAMA] The past can be
influenced by the future?
Is that even possible?
Karasu!
[NOEIN]
You should forget about him.
Because to you,
he is merely an illusion.
He's not! I don't believe it.
[NOEIN] Then go find out
for yourself, Haruka.
[HARUKA]
You are always there for me.
I'm going out for a second!
[HARUKA gasps]
[KARASU] What do you intend
to do with the Dragon Torque?
[HARUKA screams]
[KARASU yells]
Help me!
[HARUKA]
Am I... Am I gonna die?
[HARUKA] Karasu is Yu...
15 years in the future. Right?
You found her.
[HARUKA]
Karasu!
[KARASU]
Ha...ruka.
Karasu!
Haruka...
What is this?
[HARUKA]
Huh? It's already 7:30!
Oh no, I overslept!
[HARUKA]
But that's another me.
Mom! Breakfast is ready, okay?
[ASUKA]
What time is it?
It's a few minutes after eight.
I have to leave
for school now. Bye.
[ASUKA]
Have fun!
Think I'll sleep
in a little bit.
[HARUKA] Today's the
last day of the semester.
That is a homeless spirit.
[MIHO]
If you talk to it,
you'll get dragged
into the spirit world!
[HARUKA]
Morning, Ai!
[AI]
Hi, Haruka!
What's all the
conversation about?
Miho is yapping about
spiritual phenomena.
So what else is new?
Good morning, everyone!
Bell's about to ring,
take your seats.
[YUKIE] I'll take summer break
consultations after homeroom.
I got a question, Miss Yukie!
[YUKIE]
Yes, Isami?
[ISAMI] Can we go on a
date during summer break?
[YUKIE] I'm so sorry...
I'm all booked up...
...for the next three years.
[ISAMI]
That's impossible...
[HARUKA] I think this
is slightly different.
[AI] Okay, it's settled.
You're coming with us
for fright night, Isami.
I'm pretty sure I'm busy.
We can't go to fright night.
We got plans.
Back me up, will ya?
Yeah right. I can't go.
I'm going to summer school.
What about me?
Yeah, nice try. Make sure
you show up, Isami.
Could it be that you're really
just a little scaredy cat?
And that you're so
incredibly frightened
that you'll just totally
pee in your pants?
What are you
talkin' about, Miho?
[MIHO]
Am I right or not?
[ISAMI]
Not!
[HARUKA]
Hey! Wait up a minute, Yu!
You've been acting kinda
weird lately. What's up?
I guess you forgot
about it then, huh?
[ISAMI]
Some friend. He's really been
kind of a buzz kill
lately, hasn't he?
He can't help it.
He's gotta study
for those middle school tests.
[HARUKA]
I remember this. But I think
there's something
different about it.
[SHINOHARA]
Nice ship, huh?
It cost a cool
125 million bucks.
It's not a passenger ship,
so it isn't that
comfortable a ride, but...
Shinohara.
[SHINOHARA]
Just take your time there.
It's easy to tell you're
really dyin' to see it.
I thought the deal was
you'd call off the experiment.
What? Was that the deal?
I somehow doubt that what I said
was that I'd
actually call it off.
Why you...
Besides that, you accepted
the money, didn't ya?
That was for the work
I'd already done!
Look, I paid you a lot of money
for your services, Doctor.
I think I'm entitled to
a little free consultation.
You see the kinda crap
I gotta put up with?
Just the other day they
had three failed tests
at the Tsukuba laboratory.
Naturally I fired 5 of
those idiots on the spot.
[MAYUZUMI]
I can't do this anymore.
If you'll excuse me...
[SHINOHARA] It's your call,
but I'm gonna do it anyway.
You can't do that, Shinohara.
The theta particles will leak
if you don't fix it first!
Is that right?
Oh well. I'll be
watching the experiment
from Tokyo anyway,
so what do I care?
[MAYUZUMI]
Wha...?
Do you want to disintegrate
the entire region?
[SHINOHARA] You know,
now that I think about it...
isn't it true your daughter
lives around here somewhere?
Come on, Doctor,
let's watch it together.
Let's see this world that
transcends time and space.
[BARON whines]
[HARUKA]
Uh-oh. I dozed off.
What time is it?
[HARUKA] That's right!
I went to Yu's summer school.
[YU] Why are you hanging
out in front of my school?
[HARUKA] I don't know.
I guess I was just bored.
[YU]
You shouldn't be here this late.
They could arrest you
for breaking curfew.
[HARUKA]
If you're so worried about that,
then you shouldn't
run away from home.
Yeah, well you're the one who
suggested it, remember?
Because you wanted to go to
your dad's place in Tokyo!
I was fighting with
my mom when I said that.
It's hard, okay.
You don't realize...
My parents are divorced,
it's confusing.
I don't know why I ever
took you seriously.
That's not nice!
[YU]
Just forget it.
[HARUKA]
Come on! Don't be mad! Okay?
[YU]
Even if I did run away,
they'd just find me
and bring me back.
I'll never get to do
anything on my own.
I should just give up now.
Please don't say that.
When you grow up,
you'll be able to go
anywhere you want to.
[YU] I just wish I
was a grown-up now!
[HARUKA]
I know.
[YU]
I hate being a child.
I just... wanna grow up
as fast as I can!
[YU sobbing]
[HARUKA]
No...
I think... I think
I'm losing it!
[YU]
Don't follow me anymore!
[HARUKA] Hey! You didn't have
to push me over, you know.
[YU]
I'm... sorry.
[HARUKA]
This is different, too.
Where's Karasu?
[HARUKA]
Hey, let's run away tomorrow.
This me that's here is...
Are you serious?
We said we'd do it...
We can leave tomorrow
morning, right?
Where are we gonna go?
Tokyo. We can go stay
there with my dad.
[HARUKA gasps]
What's wrong?
I don't know.
[HARUKA] I feel like
I'm forgetting something.
[HARUKA]
Something important.
Who is that?
[HARUKA]
I don't remember...
[NOEIN]
You will forget.
Did you ever get
ahold of your dad?
Did he say anything about
you running away?
I guess I ran away from home.
[TIME DRIFTER]
Is that the dimension you want?
Huh?
The decision's yours to make.
Is that the dimension that
you have chosen to live in?
Is it your desire to
settle for this reality?
What are you talking about?
My choice...?
[HARUKA]
Karasu came from the future.
But I'm sure I know who he is!
[HARUKA]
He always protects me.
[ATORI]
Haha! Die!
Fukuro!
[HARUKA] But someday...
Karasu will leave me.
[HARUKA] After all,
there can only be one Yu.
[KARASU] Was I saved
by Haruka once again?
Huh?
It's like it was the last time.
[KARASU] I was supposed
to die in that battle.
[FUKURO]
Don't let it reach the ground!
[KOSAGI]
Where is Karasu?
[FUKURO]
Go around to the left!
[KOSAGI]
Not again! It has a shield!
[FUKURO]
Karasu has jumped on!
[KARASU grunting]
[KARASU screams]
[FUKURO] It's no good!
It's collapsing! Get out now!
Karasu!
[KARASU] When I passed through
the dimensional ravine...
...I arrived here.
But what I didn't
realize was that
I had been transported
to another nearby dimension.
My life was saved by being
drawn into this world.
But because I...
transported here...
...La'cryma found out
about this reality,
and learned about
the existence of Haruka.
So... It's possible I drew
another dimension here.
They want...
[YU gasps]
[KARASU gasps]
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA gasps]
Where am I?
[MIHO]
They're here! They're here!
I can feel their presence.
[ISAMI] Cut it out, Miho.
You're freakin' me out.
[MIHO]
What are you talking about?
We are trying to meet ghosts.
Could you please be
a little more serious.
And how do I do that?
[MIHO] Sense them. Chant from
the bottom of your heart.
Now! Mr. Ghost, Mr. Ghost!
Please come out!
She's impossible.
[AI]
It shouldn't bother you.
Huh?
There's nothing we
can do. His mom wouldn't
let him come out with us anyway.
I guess so.
Hey, cheer up, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Mhmm.
[AI] Come on, let's go.
We'll get left behind.
Hey, Ai, I have this feeling
I'm forgetting something
that's really important.
[NOEIN]
Haruka.
[ISAMI]
Can we go home now?
[MIHO] No! I am not going
home until I see a ghost!
[ISAMI]
Come on already!
Something's
definitely different.
It shouldn't be this way.
You're right!
There's no such thing
as a graveyard without ghosts!
[HARUKA gasps]
It's coming this way!
What's that?
--We have to run!
--What are we running from?
Hurry come on, we have
to get outta here now!
[MIHO]
Something is flying right at us!
[ISAMI]
That's impossible!
[HARUKA]
Everybody run for it!
[NOEIN]
There she is!
Just impossible.
A ghost! A land bound spirit!
What's going on here?
[HARUKA]
He's after me! Alright...
Go that way!
[NOEIN]
I finally found you, Haruka.
Stay back!
Huh?
[NOEIN] So... you've assimilated
with yourself of this dimension.
[NOEIN] It's alright now.
Come along, let's go home.
But... But who are you?
[NOEIN]
Oh, Haruka, have you forgotten?
[NOEIN] If you return
with me, you will remember.
[NOEIN] Now come. Come back
with me to Shangri-la.
[YU]
Haruka!!
Yu!
Who are you?
Tell me now.
[NOEIN]
Who, me?
[NOEIN cackles]
[NOEIN]
Do you want to know?
[YU]
I said tell me.
[NOEIN] Are you sure
you really want to know?
Who are you?
[NOEIN]
If you wish.
Just tell me.
[NOEIN]
I... am you.
[HARUKA gasps]
Run, Haruka! Go on!
[HARUKA] This isn't
where I was... and I...
I think I was forgetting
something important.
[HARUKA] I remember!
This is where I met Karasu!
[HARUKA] But it wasn't the first
time. I met him once before.
[HARUKA] It was almost spring,
but it was snowing that day...
...at that church.
[NOEIN] What is happening? The
dimension is becoming warped.
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Oh, Yu. Once again,
you tried to rescue me.
[HARUKA]
Thanks.
[YU]
It-It's no big deal.
He was worried about you, too.
[HARUKA]
Who?
Karasu!
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[KOSAGI] It doesn't matter,
even if I disappear.
[HARUKA]
Whoever you are, don't do this!
[KOSAGI]
Then fight me, Karasu!
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "Dilemma."
Can you look within yourself?