[ATORI]
Haruka, somebody's here!
[HARUKA]
What is it, Atori?
Did you hear somebody pull up?
Umm...
[HARUKA]
Huh. I don't see anyone.
[ATORI]
They were here.
Who was here?
But they didn't
hang around very long.
Well, Kosagi, feeling better?
Calmer, sir, if you care.
We need to secure
the Dragon Torque.
It is the solitary mission
bestowed upon us
as Dragon Soldiers.
It's impossible for you
to capture it by yourself.
[KOSAGI] If I hadn't been
forcefully retransported,
I would have secured her.
It must be approached
with caution.
The Dragon Torque has started
to have a will of its own.
It doesn't matter
what happens to me,
as long as I secure--
[KUINA]
That's enough!
You don't get it.
[KOSAGI] We both know that
La'cryma can't survive
without the Dragon Torque.
[KUINA] That's not it!
Why can't you understand?!
[KOSAGI]
Wha--?!
[KUINA]
I don't care what happens
to the world of La'cryma...
...because I need you.
[KOSAGI]
Wha-What?
[KUINA]
I don't wanna lose you...
Kuina!
[KUINA] I want to live my
life with you, Kosagi...
[knocking]
[MIYUKI]
Can I come in?
Oh, looks like another nice day.
[MIYUKI] So, you've been
studying very hard.
[YU]
Yeah.
[MIYUKI]
And, how's it going?
[YU]
Fine...
Need a break? If you'd like,
you could help me
with the storage room.
[YU]
I don't know...
I can't really lift all those
heavy things by myself.
Yeah, I guess so, Mom.
[MIYUKI]
Um, Yu?
[YU]
Huh?
This is your last summer break
before you become a teenager.
I guess so. I'm going
to be 13 next year.
That's why I think you should do
everything you wanna
do this summer break.
Have all the fun
you can squeeze in.
[YU] There's nothing
I really wanna do.
You need to enjoy
your childhood, young man.
I'll do stuff after I get
through with all the exams.
But...
Hey, Mom, what's this thing?
[MIYUKI]
What?
Oh, the video camera.
Really?
Yes, your father bought it
when you came home
from the hospital.
Man, it's huge!
It was pretty expensive too!
I don't know about this...
[YU sighs]
Boring.
What? A wedding?
[HARUKA]
For your mom and dad?
[MIHO] So why are they
having a wedding now?
[AI] Apparently,
when they got married,
Mom decided not
to have a wedding
because it was too expensive.
It's always bothered Dad
that they couldn't afford it.
And now they'll have
the wedding of their dreams!
How romantic!
It's cool because they
still get along really well.
That's true! They always
seem so happy together!
I know she's going
to be absolutely stunning
in her wedding dress!
Tres bien!
It's true, Ai.
Your mom's really pretty.
And nice too.
Yeah, but it took her awhile.
Huh?
There's another reason why
they didn't have a wedding.
I hope it's a good one.
You got it.
[MIHO]
What is that?
Oh, she is so cool!
No way this is your mother!
[MIHO squeals]
[AI] This picture was
taken when she was still
in high school,
way before they met.
And my dad is completely
clueless about all of it.
[MIHO]
Lemme see it again, will ya?
[HARUKA] Wow, your mom
just got even cooler!
[ISAMI] Hey, whatcha
lookin' at? Lemme see!
[AI]
Oh, no way!
[ISAMI]
Oh, impossible.
[AI gasps]
Hey...
[AI]
Where'd you get that thing?
[YU]
I found it at home.
[MIHO]
Wow, that's professional!
I guess it is.
So, do you know how to use it?
[YU]
Sorta...
Hey, I got an idea!
How'd you like to be
a cameraman at a wedding?
Someone's getting married?
Yeah, Ai's mother
and father are.
And we happen to be
looking for someone to shoot it.
So will you do it?
[YU]
Uh, yeah, I guess so.
[ISAMI]
Cameraman, huh?
Hey that's cool.
Good luck with that.
What's wrong?
It disappeared...
[KOORIYAMA]
Are they out there, Uchida?
[UCHIDA] Yes, one, two,
three, four, five...
They're all there.
How unusual. They're all
together again.
[UCHIDA]
I didn't think the lab boats
would get here so quickly.
[KOORIYAMA] Shinohara must've
sent for them well in advance.
It was his plan
to quash the Ab Com
investigation results
from the get-go.
And on top of that,
he used it
to move the project forward.
Him again?
I have to stop this.
There's no way he can use this
location of continuous
abnormal quantum
potential fluctuation to
activate the Magic Circle!
I believe there's an old
saying that goes:
"Arrogance is the path
that leads to self-destruction."
Kooriyama?
I suppose in the long run,
it's our fault.
We, as adults, are living
proof of that arrogance.
But what we can't do
is destroy the future
for our children.
[TOBI] Haruka's power
may be accelerating.
[KARASU] You think she's making
the dimensions come together?
[TOBI]
That's highly probable.
Hey, Karasu?
[HARUKA] Was the strange
dimension I saw
the world you call "Shangri-la?"
That was about the same
time I started seeing
all those other people.
What people?
Well, they're not really people.
Shangri-la...
[HARUKA]
Do you think so?
I think they wanna meet me.
Um, but the guy also said
that I would eventually
come to a place
called Shangri-la.
The man in the mask?
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[TOBI] The appearance rates
at the zero point
are increasing tremendously.
It might be linked to that.
It's possible that the
errosion of Shangri-la
may already have started
in this dimension.
[OPERATOR] Commence revision
of coordinates X-X-X.
Countdown.
5... 4... 3... 2... 1... 0...
[KUINA]
What are you looking at?!
I mean, what can
you see, Kosagi?
I see... nothing.
We don't have the ability
to observe those coordinates.
That's true... Perhaps we
shouldn't see them.
[OPERATOR]
W-2 is gone. Cool-down.
[KOSAGI] It's happening again...
Observers are falling apart
one after the other.
[KUINA] The dimensional
waiver is accelerating.
[KUINA] The lines have
reached their limit.
[KOSAGI] We must secure
the Dragon Torque immediately!
Nothing more can be
done for La'cryma.
I found something unusual.
Is this lipstick?
I will find a dimension
where we can live together...
[KOSAGI]
You two wait here for me.
[DRAGON SOLDIERS]
Yes ma'am.
[KOSAGI] Your expulsion from
the elite dwelling quarters
to this place is
your punishment.
How could you allow
the Dragon Torque
and Karasu to escape?
It is only by the mercy
of the leadership department
that you were not eliminated.
[AMAMIKU]
I do not regret my decision.
Uh?
When you see there's a mistake,
I do not think it is
wrong to correct it.
[KOSAGI] We are fighting to
keep La'cryma in existence!
You people have acted
idiotically and lost
the possibility of a future
by allowing yourselves
to be blinded by the past!
[AMAMIKU]
That's not true, Kosagi.
What?!
[AMAMIKU]
To regret the past,
is to never repeat
the same mistake.
The Dragon Torque has given us
this unique opportunity.
To correct the errors we made.
I can't believe how
confused you've become!
Don't you see-- it's only a
dimension we've simulated!
The Dragon Torque
itself is no more
than a body of enery
created by a quantum spin.
Believing it is a
human being is merely
the result of
existential interference.
[AMAMIKU]
Maybe. Except for the fact
that I recognized that
girl as Haruka.
[KOSAGI gasps]
And I can tell you
she recognized me.
She called me by my real name.
But... because of her,
Karasu and Fukuro
fought with each other...
...and Fukuro died.
[AMAMIKU gasps]
[KOSAGI]
Kuina!
You're...
I have a favor
I want to ask you.
Let me go and defeat Karasu.
Kosagi...
I want to settle it.
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL A]
I'm so tired. This sucks.
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL B]
Yeah really!
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRLS giggling]
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL A] They think
they're, like, so hot.
[AI] Hey, Miss
Incosiderate, get a clue!
You're hitting someone
with your leg!
Huh?! Who's this chick?!
Well? Apologize to her!
It's alright young lady.
[AI]
It's not alright!
Go on back to middle school!
Hey! I'm in elementary school!
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRLS laugh]
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL B] No way!
She's totally, like, a kid!
And she thinks she can
tell us what to do!
Actually, I do! So why don't
you learn some manners?
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL A]
Huh?
Why don't you come
for a walk with us, little girl?
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRLS giggle]
[ISAMI]
Huh?
Hey, is that Ai?
[AI] What are you doing?!
Let go of me!
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL A] Don't mess
with us, you little bitch.
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL B]
We oughta teach her a lesson.
[ISAMI]
Hey!
[GIRLS gasp]
[ISAMI]
What're you doing here?
Who're these chicks?
New friends?
Oh, you're all
impossibly hot! I mean it!
How you doin'? I'm her
classmate, known her for years!
So, which high school
is it you ladies go to?
Because I'm goin' there!
You're smokin'!
Talk about eye-candy!
[HGHSCHOOL GIRLS laugh]
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL A]
Who is this weird kid?
Did he actually
call us "eye-candy"?
He's like Fujiwara!
Or his kid brother!
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRLS laugh]
[ISAMI laughs nervously]
I've laughed so hard,
now I'm bored with him.
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL A]
Let's go.
[HIGHSCHOOL GIRL C]
Yeah, let's get outta here.
So lame.
Bye-bye. Yeah.
What the heck is
wrong with you, huh?!
Those aren't girls
you wanna hang out with!
I just--
You probably told them
they were being
rude or something!
Look, Ai, you gotta
pick your battles!
I didn't mean to yell.
It's not your fault.
The only reason I know about 'em
is because of my idiot brother.
[AI]
Sorry...
I'm sorry.
C'mon, don't cry.
[AI]
But I was so scared of them.
Then why didn't you cry sooner?
I know somebody
would've come over
and given you some help.
I refuse to let jerks like
that make me cry, okay?
Why would you say that?
That really doesn't
make any sense.
[ISAMI]
Here, you can use this.
It's dirty.
Fine! Okay, then don't!
Or... do. I don't care.
You're impossible.
I appreciate it.
Eh, it's nothin'.
--[AI] Isami...
--[ISAMI] Hm?
Thanks for bailing me out.
Anytime.
[AMAMIKU]
I pray that Fukuro's Reizu
will come to rest in
a beautiful place...
[TOBI] The abnormal range of
the location is spreading again.
[KARASU]
The dimensional interference
is probably getting worse.
And yet, it still
looks so peaceful.
I'm jealous of
your past, Karasu.
It's only an approximation.
My actual time has not
appeared precisely yet.
[TOBI] That may be, but it
is infinitely close, right?
[TOBI] The place where I was
raised... was so horrible.
[TOBI] But... I've already
forgotten about those times.
[TOBI]
It's the same for Atori.
[TOBI gasps]
[KARASU gasps]
What's this?!
An undulation! The dimension
is shaking, Karasu!
[KARASU]
This sensation...
[TOBI gasps]
It's La'cryma!
[KARASU]
Tobi, I'm going in now!
[ASUKA] Now I want you to behave
yourself like the lady you are.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, I know. By the way,
you sure this is gonna be okay?
It doesn't look weird
from the back, does it?
Ooh... It's perfect.
You look great.
Really?
Really. It's sweet.
I could eat you up.
Yeah?
You're a cutie, Haruka.
Definitely my girl.
[HARUKA]
You're embarassing me.
See you later!
[ASUKA]
Be careful now!
[HARUKA gasps]
What's this?!
Has it actually gotten stronger?
[KOSAGI]
It looks just like a child!
The Torque is simply
a convergence of
high-density energy.
If I can just contain
the volatile reaction...
Did you come here
from the future too?
[KOSAGI gasps]
Please don't fight with Karasu.
[HARUKA] I don't want him
to have to fight anymore.
How did you--
[HARUKA gasps]
Karasu!
It stopped...
[KOSAGI] You traitor!
I will never forgive you!
I swear I'll take
you down... with me!
Go home, Kosagi.
It's pointless for
the two of us to fight.
[KOSAGI]
Karasu!
Are you the one
who killed Fukurou?
I'm not.
[KOSAGI] Even if you weren't,
I will destroy you.
[KARASU]
I cannot disappear yet.
[KOSAGI]
Then fight me, Karasu!
Come on, fight!
Why won't you face me?!
You cannot fight
in your current state.
You're a traitor! You are
nothing but a coward
who betrayed his allies for
an illusion of the past!
[KOSAGI]
I will never forgive you!
[TOBI]
Stop this, Kosagi.
[KOSAGI]
Move!
There's nothing
to gain by killing us.
Doing so won't save La'cryma.
By using the
Dragon Torque's powers,
we can stop the
errosion of Shangri-la!
[TOBI] You're wrong.
Dragon Torque's energy
is not meant to be
used for that purpose.
[TOBI]
I believe it has appeared
to restore every
warped dimension.
[TOBI]
I don't think it's a coincidence
that we found it here.
It is a necessity
for every dimension.
That's enough lies!
Besides, you know
you can't kill Karasu.
[KOSAGI gasps]
[TOBI]
Be honest with yourself.
Now it's gone...
Karasu! Return to La'cryma!
Kosagi!
[KOSAGI] You are
well aware that by staying
unconnected to the pipeline
that you will eventually
vanish from this world.
I will protect Haruka.
Karasu... You care
for her that much...
[KARASU gasps]
No, don't!
[KARASU grunts]
[OPERATOR]
The pipeline has been cut off.
She didn't...!
[KARASU]
Kosagi...
I want to be there...
when you die.
[HARUKA]
Baron...
[YU]
Haruka?
Hey, something wrong?
I'm waiting. For Karasu.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[AI] Doesn't look
like a plane, does it?
[KUINA yells]
[KUINA groans]
[NOEIN] You can also
collapse and die.
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "Nightmare."
Is the world you
live in a reality?