[ATORI]
What are you doing?!
Finish him off already!
We can't waste any more
time in a dump like this!
Atori!
I'll handle this.
[ATORI yells]
[ATORI]
Karasu.
I'll take these guys,
you get going.
What?
[ATORI]
Don't argue!
Go and save Haruka.
Get going.
Thank you.
Now, let's blow
Shangri-la back to Hell!
Come to me, Dragon Torque.
Come with me to a
world of nothingness.
Haruka!
Come...
[NOEIN]
My Dragon Torque...
[ATORI]
What--?
Huh...?
All particles now
approaching light speed.
[SHINOHARA]
What is that?
Is the mountain on fire?!
The dimensions are
overlapping! My god!
[OPERATOR 1]
Critical mass!
Theta particle
generation in process.
Outbreak, mark one-twenty.
These numbers are
incredibly abnormal!
What are your readings?
The instruments don't
seem to be right!
[OPERATOR 2] Computer
calculation speed falling.
[OPERATOR 4]
All coordinates lost.
[SHINOHARA]
Dammit! What is wrong?!
What the hell is it?! Everything
was going so well up until now!
The critical stage is
beginnin' to consume us...
[SHINOHARA]
Who gives a crap?!
They're just these
little particles!
More bad news:
the voltage is dropping!
The coil is starting to degauss!
[OPERATOR 3]
We've lost all satellites!
What, Dr. Mayuzumi?
The place site is in the process
of achieving a quantum state.
Don't screw with me!
What the hell does that mean?!
Soon, all existences will
become de-established and--
Better knock that off, now!
It's impossible for a
macro world like ours
to achieve a quantum state!
You're wrong,
but that's not all.
This may be leading to
the worst-case scenario.
Dimensional convergence...
When you forcefully establish
something that has not been
established in previous
dimensions then--
Then what, Doctor?!
[UCHIDA]
It will disappear.
[SHINOHARA]
Huh?!
By forcibly merging infinite
choices simultaneously,
a place site will occur,
forcin' the infinite
dimensions into convergence.
Everything drawn into
that place site will...
...disappear.
What are you talkin' about...?
[OPERATOR 1]
No!
[OPERATOR 3]
What's that?!
It's that ring we saw before!
Well, why'd it have
to show up again?!
What is that thing?
Must be a mirage of some kind...
That's not right...
[AI] Look, the center of that
thing is starting to glow!
[ISAMI] I see something
there! Impossible...
Shangri-la, is that it?
[ISAMI] Hey, come on,
let's go up the mountain!
[AI] Okay, we can get a
better look from up there!
[MIHO]
Hurry, hurry!
[YUKIE] Hey, where are
you going? Just hold on!
Huh?
Where am I?
Where is this place?
[TIME DRIFTER]
Haruka...
Yu...
[TIME DRIFTER]
That's right.
You're here?
[TIME DRIFTER] The poor fellow.
He has chosen that dimension.
[TIME DRIFTER] It is a future
full of hate and sorrow.
Future?
Yes. It is one of many futures.
Then, what should I do?
[TIME DRIFTER]
That depends.
What sort of future
would you like to see?
Well, I know I don't
wanna see a sad future.
[TIME DRIFTER]
Multiple dimensions create
an infinite choice of futures,
so people can imagine
better existences.
[HARUKA] What if there
were only one future?
[TIME DRIFTER] Dimensions
without options would collapse
and cease to be.
[HARUKA]
Would... everyone disappear?
[TIME DRIFTER]
Yes.
The Earth and the sky
would disappear.
All would return to the void.
Well, then what should I do?
[TIME DRIFTER] From all the
dimensions, you were chosen.
How come?
[TIME DRIFTER] It is possible,
it didn't have to be you...
[TIME DRIFTER]
But you were the one chosen.
[HARUKA]
I'm going to decide?
[TIME DRIFTER] You must
listen to all the dimensions.
To the voices of
all living things.
Feel them.
I have to feel... everything?
This is the end!
It's the end of the world!
Everything's gonna disappear!
[AMAMIKU]
Lily! Open the door, Lily!
Auntie, hello.
Lily, go and get your mother.
Everything's gonna
disappear, isn't it?
We don't know that for sure.
We need to go to the surface.
[LILY]
Huh?
All of us. We need
to see the world.
We must have the courage to
really look at our world again.
And then we will be
able to recognize it.
[CHILD A] You're late, Atori.
Where've you been?
[CHILD B]
Sara says that supper's ready.
[SARA]
Welcome back, Big Brother.
[ATORI]
Sara!
No! There's no way I
will disappear just yet!
It won't go that way!
[KOSAGI]
Is it hopeless?
Will Shangri-la swallow them?
There's got to be another way.
[TOBI] Take this,
you return to La'cryma.
[KOSAGI]
The storage battery...
It's too late to
return to La'cryma!
Right now,
every single dimension
is being drawn into the tide
of Shangri-la's causation.
Its causation?
If we can somehow
manage to oppose it,
there's the possibility
we may be able
to cancel the
Omni-dimensional integration.
We can push it back?
[KOSAGI] You mean destroy
the Reizu simulator?
[TOBI]
That's right.
[KOSAGI]
The existence descriptive data
for the world of
La'cryma will be lost!
[TOBI]
No it won't.
It's completely useless
to create a virtual observer
using the Reizu system.
To establish existence,
the most vital aspect
is that people observe
others and acknowledge them.
If people can recognize
and understand each other,
existence can be established.
Tobi...
[TOBI] I realized it when
I came to this dimension
and met Haruka.
I saw how people can
become established
by having their
existence recognized.
[ISAMI] Look out, comin'
through here! Excuse me!
Hey, the light's definitely
brighter over here!
And you can see it better!
And Haruka's trapped inside
that thing, isn't she?
Look, what's that?!
[ISAMI]
Those things are impossible!
Haruka's coming back to us,
I'm sure of that!
Of course she will.
Atori and Karasu are with her.
That's right. And Yu's
comin' back too. I believe it.
That is the Uroborus.
Huh? Wow...
[LILY] It's so pretty. I wish
you could see it, Mommy.
[MIHO] What do you see?
Describe it to me, Lily.
There's this huge ring
floating in the sky, and then,
you can see all this pretty
scenery inside of it.
[KOSAGI] I guess this
place is abandoned now.
[WOMAN]
What is that?!
All of the dimensions
are linked up.
[MIHO]
They're all coming this way!
[ISAMI]
Impossible!
[AI]
What now?!
They seem to be
looking right at us!
What the heck is that?
Whatever it is,
it's really tough.
That's Atori!
It's him, he's come to help!
He said he would
protect us, didn't he?
[NOEIN cackles]
And here you are.
I have the powers of the Dragon
Torque to use as I see fit.
[NOEIN]
The dimensions are now
on their way
towards integration.
[KARASU]
How could you?
The end of everything has begun.
And then, it's done.
Isn't that what you were
wishing for all along?
After all, we're one
and the same.
You feel it? All of
the pain, all the rage.
People are so foolish.
I wish I had never come to know
the meaning of existence.
[ATORI]
Blast! This isn't working!
They are swarming like a virus!
They're everywhere!
[OPERATOR 1] Neither first
nor second system can reboot!
[OPERATOR 2]
Third system is down, too!
I don't know what's
happening here...
[OPERATOR 1]
But the particles are continuing
to accelerate, aren't they?
Why don't you try rebooting?
[OPERATOR 3]
What's going on?!
[OPERATOR 2]
There's two of me!
What the--?! This isn't real!
It appears as if all
dimensions are converging!
[UCHIDA]
Can't be!
[KOORIYAMA]
What's happening?
Uchida, is this
another after-effect
of this dimension thing?
[UCHIDA]
Kooriyama?!
[KOORIYAMA]
Is that... me?
It's chaos!
I'm looking at another me!
This is nuts!
[KOORIYAMA] So this is what you
meant about rolling snake eyes.
So I guess there's another me
that just can't be shot.
Wh-What're you--?!
No! What're you gonna do?!
[KOORIYAMA] Shut up,
you annoying little bastard!
And apparently,
it hurts my hand to hit
this little twerp
in any dimension.
Thanks, Kooriyama.
Unfortunately, it's going to
take more than hitting Shinohara
to get us out of this.
Uh-huh.
[TOBI] There's still a way...
We can't give up...
[UCHIDA]
Tobi...
[MIHO]
It's Atori...
[AI] He's stopping those guys
from coming out of the circle!
That dude's just
totally awesome!
[HARUKA] I think that, really,
I was happy. In every dimension.
And because I met you,
I've always been happy.
But you're not like Karasu.
You forgot, didn't you?
I have never forgotten
what happened!
I can still remember the flames,
as if it were yesterday!
I have not forgotten
what I felt...
No! You have Yu's memories,
but you've forgotten them.
[YU] Haruka... Y'know, I think I
like it here better than Tokyo.
I'm more... relaxed.
[YU] It's been almost
four years... since you died.
Time flies...
[HARUKA]
The Haruka of this dimension
is no longer here either.
He has not forgotten me.
It's not true! I have
not forgotten you!
[HARUKA]
You are not like Karasu.
[NOEIN]
I haven't!
[HARUKA]
You've forgotten me...
[THE OTHERS A]
Stop this, now.
[THE OTHERS B]
Stop obliterating everything.
[NOEIN]
Shut up, scum!
You insignificant people
ran away from the pain of life!
All of you can rot away
in your imaginary paradise!
We must oppose the tide even
if we're the only dimension.
We must stop the Magic Circle
and pull out of
the quantum state.
Tobi, we're ready! I've gotten
the back-up computer booted up.
Miss Uchida.
I know.
When the Magic
Circle disappears,
I will need to
observe the Kooriyama
who wasn't shot in
order to... establish him
Hey, it'll be alright.
I'm thinkin' God'll give me
a good roll of the dice.
I cannot let them down!
Now!
The program has started running!
Dr. Mayuzumi!
Emergency shut down!
[NOEIN yells]
It can't be!
You won't go away...
[NOEIN] You can't possibly
hope to destroy me.
You know that you and I
are the same being.
You and I will
never be the same!
[NOEIN]
It can't be! All the dimensions
should've converged by now.
[YU]
I saw your past.
[YU] Perhaps I was your past.
But right now...
...you're not me!
If you were me, I wouldn't
have forgotten about Haruka!
I wouldn't have
killed Isami, either!
Yes, you would,
because you are me.
No! We are not the same person!
I will never
become what you are!
I won't give up on the future!
Your existence has not
been established by anyone.
You are nothing but an illusion!
I'm an illusion...?
Come with me, Haruka.
We'll go home together.
You're here!
[AMAMIKU]
The Uroboros is fading...
Oh no, Atori...
[CROWD]
What's that?
Is that snow?
[ASUKA]
Snow?
[MIYUKI]
Blue snow?
Wow...
That's interesting.
I've never seen that before.
Atori...
[ISAMI]
It's beautiful.
[UCHIDA]
Kooriyama!
Oh, thank God!
Take it easy there, Uchida.
Tell me, did we avert the
dimensional convergence?!
[TOBI]
Dr. Mayuzumi...
It's alright...
The balance is
being maintained...
[MAYUZUMI]
Tobi!
May be there be happiness...
in your dimension's future...
[UCHIDA] Tobi! Kooriyama
is back to normal. He--
[UCHIDA]
...Tobi?
[NOEIN]
Who am I?
No one chose to recognize me
in any of these dimensions...?
My existence will not
be established...?
[THE OTHERS A]
The time of assembly has ended.
[THE OTHERS B] The place site
of selection is revived.
[THE OTHERS A]
Recognition has been restored.
You had no choice
in this matter...
I had control of everything...
[NOEIN] You will all be
back to this dimension...
[NOEIN]
...again...
What's this? Where am I?
[KARASU]
The dimensional horizon.
[HARUKA]
Karasu!
[KARASU]
The dimensions are restored.
The future has
gained infinite choice.
[HARUKA] So, the future's path
has not been decided, right?
[KARASU]
That's right, Haruka.
I'm glad!
Aren't you gonna stay with me?
[KARASU] I'll always be with you
and protect you. I swear it.
Will I see you again?
In fifteen years.
Ah, because you're Yu!
That's right.
Ah, Haruka!
Hey, I just heard
Haruka's voice!
[ISAMI]
Me too! She said she's with Yu!
[MIHO]
More blue snow.
[AI, ISAMI]
Huh?
Haruka.
Yu.
I-I, um...
[AI]
Haruka!
[ISAMI]
Yu!
[MIHO]
Haruka!
[ISAMI]
This is impossible!
[AI]
Haruka, you're alright!
[ISAMI]
Totally unbelievably impossible!
[YU] Isami, it's alright!
Don't worry!
[AI]
Thank goodness!
[ISAMI]
Im-possible!
[YU]
Really, it's alright!
[MIHO]
Hey!
[AI] Haruka, is Yu coming
back home from Tokyo?
[HARUKA]
It looks that way.
[MIHO] That's great! It's been
a long time, huh, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
But we always exchange e-mails.
[AI] Alright! I'll call Isami
and we'll all get together!
[MIHO]
Now you sound just as excited.
[HARUK] I'm just going
to swing by the church.
[AI]
Oh, okay. See ya, Haruka!
[MIHO]
Bye!
Karasu...
[HARUKA]
Yu is coming home soon.