[FUKURO]
So, what's it gonna be?
[KARASU] If you try to
take the Dragon Torque,
I'll have to fight you.
[FUKURO] You've really
lost it, my old friend.
Do you really think
you can take me?
In the shape you're in?
I was hoping to avoid this.
Wait, look at that.
The wavering in this world
is getting a lot worse.
[KARASU] Because La'cryma
interfered with it.
You realize if this
dimension is blown apart,
the Dragon Torque
will be lost.
[KARASU]
I won't let that happen.
I'll protect Haruka.
I am not going to
let you take her.
[FUKURO chuckles]
Now that you've cut yourself
off from the pipeline,
you're eventually
going to die anyway.
[KOSAGI grunting]
It's your fault Haruka.
[FUKURO]
Well, after you're gone,
we can take our time
securing the Dragon Torque.
I guess our epic battle
will have to wait, right?
[HARUKA sighs]
[KARASU panting]
[HARUKA]
Karasu!
What is it?
[KUINA groans]
Hey, wait just a minute!
Why did you just
force that recall?
I had an unexpected
situation to deal with.
But I had her. I was so close.
[KOORIYAMA] What's Shinohara
got such a big ego for?
He's just the president
of some small
telecommunications company.
[UCHIDA] Well, we're gonna
have to deal with it.
His company invested
one third of the funds
for the Magic Circle.
[KOORIYAMA]
Yeah, but thought your Ab-Com
is supposed to be
supervising the project.
Isn't that right?
[UCHIDA]
We're just a nuisance.
If he controls the
prelim investigation
than he's the one
who can proceed.
He simply wants the
glory of performin'
the quantum teleportation
test himself.
Quantum teleportation?
[UCHIDA]
If you make an alteration
to a single simultaneous
regenerative quantum,
then the same alteration
will occur to other quanta.
We call this
quantum teleportation.
It's a system that uses
the properties of
quanta to instantaneously
send large quantities
of information.
It's the Magic Circle Project
the government is
workin' on now.
We took it further.
We directed our attention to
the theta particles
of quanta in particular.
They're probably the
smallest unit of matter.
The government
is thinkin' about
applying our research
to teleportation.
If it works, they say
it will change the world
in far greater ways than
the industrial revolution.
[KOORIYAMA]
Hmmm...
Quanta, huh?
Is it dangerous?
Theta particals influence
the location of
the quantum potential.
I'm really not following you.
To put in in layman's terms:
Dimensions become twisted.
They what?
I have a feeling that all
of the unexplained events
we're experiencing
are the result
of contact with
other dimensions.
[KOORIYAMA]
Other dimensions?
Can you explain this so
that I can understand it?
Other dimensions, as in,
the multiuniverse interpretation
of quantum theory.
The multiplex
universal quadrophonic.
Who doesn't know about that?
God's not someone
who rolls the dice.
What's that mean?
It's just a metaphor
for people like you
who don't believe
in the uncertainity
of a quantum world.
[KOORIYAMA] Okay, now you've
completely lost me.
Let's suppose you
roll a single die
and it comes up a six.
I prefer ones myself.
They're more lucky.
[UCHIDA]
All right, a one it is.
So let's say you rolled a one,
but you also could have
rolled a four or a five.
All the odds are
exactly the same.
Do you follow?
[KOORIYAMA]
I guess so.
But what if there were worlds
where you rolled a four
and a five as well?
Huh?
[UCHIDA sighs]
You see, there are
countless worlds
where your countless
self is rolling
countless amounts of dice.
What? Are you tellin' me
that you believe
this sort of thing?
[UCHIDA] Let me try to
explain this to you.
The tiniest elementary quanta
that compose matter
are just too small
to be observed in
their natural state.
[KOORIYAMA] So you're
saying that the microscope
to see something that small
hasn't been invented yet?
[UCHIDA]
Actually, there's more to it.
[UCHIDA] In order for humans
to observe these objects,
we must hit it with light
and observe it's reflection.
However, the quanta are almost
the same size as the
photons that create light.
So hitting them with
light has a large effect
on the quanta we are observin'.
[KOORIYAMA] Okay, okay.
I understand that part.
You can't properly
observe this stuff.
But what does that
have to do with
these other worlds
being out there?
How does all that
figure into this?
[UCHIDA] Not bein' able
to observe them means
that we can't tell what state
the quanta are in
at any given time.
In other words, infinite
possibilities will exist.
What the hell does that mean?
[UCHIDA] Okay, uhmm, take
grains of sand on a beach.
Even though we can't
see them all, they exist
in every dimension
on every beach,
but just maybe not
in the same place.
[KOORIYAMA] So you're saying
that although we can't see it
there's a possibility that it
exists in other dimensions?
[UCHIDA]
Take it further.
What if those grains of sand
were somethin' else entirely?
[KOORIYAMA]
Something else?
Yes, you see, all of the
matter in this world,
includin' you and I, are
made from accumulations
of these small quanta,
but they don't have to be
the same in each world.
[KOORIYAMA]
Hold on a second.
So you're saying that the
location of these things
isn't even definite,
so I might not even be me?
But I'm standing right here,
and this table and that glass
are right in front of me.
I'm afraid that is
where the theories
of quantum physics become
kind of difficult to explain.
[UCHIDA]
Even if existance is steadfast
on an everyday macro level,
the moment it's taken to
the quantum micro level
it's existance
becomes ambiguous.
[KOORIYAMA]
You're giving me a headache.
[UCHIDA]
It's simple.
If you believe this world
consists of unstable quanta,
then it's possible to believe
that this entire universe
is branchin' off
moment by moment
into infinte universes
with unlimited possibilities.
So is that what
you were talking about
when you said there
were other dimensions
that are in existence
where I don't roll a one?
[UCHIDA] In quantum
mechanics there is a theory
known as the
multiverse interpretation,
in which countless
worlds are lined up
in an endless row
like opposin' mirrors
where countless selves
are rolling countless dice.
You seriously believe in
all this multi-quantum
universal crap, Uchida?
[UCHIDA]
Yes, as a matter of fact, I do.
We call them
alternate dimensions.
In a quantum world, there is
only one other coordinate
that will transcend
all of time and space.
The equation that
indicates that coordinate
is proof of the existance
of alternate dimensions.
Although it's existence
is strictly numerical.
Is there a possibility
that we could
travel to one of these places?
[UCHIDA]
It might be possible
if we could become
a quantum existence.
Becoming an uncertain
existence to travel
to an uncertain
alternate dimension
may theorectically be possible.
[KOORIYAMA] I feel like
I have a bad hangover.
[UCHIDA] Look, a long time
ago people used to believe
the sun revolved
around the earth.
It took them a while
to accept the truth.
It just takes time.
When somethin' is
ingrained in people's brains
as common sense, it takes
time to change them.
Yes, it'll take me a while.
If the universe is really
how you think it is,
then what's gonna
happen after this?
[UCHIDA] The stability of the
quantum dimensions will be lost,
and every dimension will expire.
And everything will be gone.
[KOORIYAMA gasps]
[ISAMI] So your mom said you
don't have to study anymore
if you don't want to.
[YU]
Something like that.
[ISAMI] Then you should come
back to the soccer team.
[YU] I told you already.
It's not fun for me.
I'm not as good as you.
[ISAMI] It's not like you
have to go pro or anything.
At the very least, you should
do it for your health.
[YU] What am I,
an old man? That's weak.
[ISAMI]
I'm just sayin'.
You don't have to have a reason.
Just play 'cause you like it.
[YU]
No thanks.
All right, then what
do you wanna do?
That's where I'm
having some trouble.
Huh?
I've been sitting here
trying to figure out
what I wanna do with my life.
[ISAMI]
And?
[YU] I don't know.
I mean, soccer's okay,
but I'm not very good at it.
[ISAMI]
You gotta practice to get good.
[YU]
Dude, I have been practicing.
Since the third grade. I stink.
[ISAMI]
Well, yeah, but--
[YU] I just really don't think
I have the talent for it.
[ISAMI]
Hm...
I thought about music, art,
maybe a different sport,
but all that stuff's
for people who were born
with the talent to do it.
[ISAMI]
That's not true!
It is, but it's okay,
because I get what
my mom was saying.
The more you study,
the more your grades go up.
Even a no talent loser
like me can do that.
[ISAMI] Yeah, but you're
great at school. I'm not.
[YU]
That's because you don't try.
All you gotta do is
give up some play time.
So that's why...
[ISAMI]
Why what?
I think, I should just
take the entrance exams.
No way, dude! If you
go to school in Tokyo,
you won't be able to hang out
with any of us anymore.
I'm not happy about that either.
Then forget about
taking those dumb exams.
Just blow 'em off.
[YU]
Just grow up, would ya?
You can't always
have it your way.
You know you can do anything
if you put your mind to it!
[YU] That's not how
the real world works.
Shut up! Shut up! I just can't
take all this negativity!
You just suck!
[ISAMI]
You're impossible!
[ATORI] Karasu, Fukuro...
Karasu, Fukuro...
Karasu, Fukuro...Karas--
[TOBI]
Would you stop pacing, Atori?
All of this worrying is going
to deplete your energy.
I will kill them!
[BARON whines]
[running steps]
[ASUKA groans]
Nn? Ahh... Huh?
[BARON whines]
[HARUKA panting]
[ASUKA sighs]
Ahh. Woo.
Huh. Something's really
bothering her.
Hmmm...
Guess I'll go make
some lunch. [yawns]
[ASUKA]
Oh, forget it...
[HARUKA panting]
[ASUKA]
Time for lunch!
Huh?!
[HARUKA] You're kidding!
You actually made lunch, Mom?
That's it?
That's it.
[ASUKA]
Well, dig in.
[HARUKA]
Kay...
Thanks a lot for
this meal. Yeah!
[HARUKA slurps]
[ASUKA]
Is it good?
Mm.
[ASUKA] Any closer
to solving your problem?
Huh?
You know, you can always
talk to me, Haruka honey,
I'd be happy to help you.
Hmmm...
I was wondering what I'll
be doing 15 years from now.
Eh. 15 years from now?!
That's sort of a strange
thing to be worried about,
don't you think?
[HARUKA] Remember when
I was a little girl,
and I used to say I
saw ghosts everywhere?
Apparently what I was
seeing was other worlds.
Uh? Did you say "other worlds"?
Yes, there are other
dimension, actually.
--[running steps approaching]
--Huh?
[TSUYOSHI]
Body slaaaaam!!
Ah!!
You're such a moron, Tsuyoshi!
Ow... Don't call your
brother a moron!!
Say uncle!!
I give up! Stop it!
I win! You're a
little nerd! Ha ha ha!
Ugh! Why don't you
pick on someone
your own size, you jerk?
[TSUYOSHI]
Hmmm...Are you okay?
What? What do ya mean?
You don't seem like
yourself. You all right?
Don't sweat it.
[TSUYOSHI]
C'mon. Tell me what's goin' on.
[ISAMI] My friend, Yu is gonna
take the exams after all.
[TSUYOSHI]
Ah, he's really smart
so he shouldn't have
any trouble gettin' in.
[ISAMI]
Yeah, I guess...
[TSUYOSHI] So you two be going
to different middle schools.
[ISAMI]
Yeah...
[TSUYOSHI]
You're gonna miss him?
[ISAMI]
Yeah...
[TSUYOSHI]
You know what?
If you little guys
are good friends,
it don't matter where you are,
you're still gonna
be good friends!
Say it! Don't spray it!
[TSUYOSHI]
Why you!
[TSUYOSHI] All I'm trying
is to give you some advice!
[ISAMI]
Ugh, that is impossible.
Huh? It's almost Obon time.
Auugh... Yeah...
[TSUYOSHI sighs]
We have to get ready
to visit Mom and Dad's graves.
Yeah, Fumiko told me she's
gonna make paper dolls again.
You're not gonna
do it this year?
I'm almost in
middle school, you know.
I got better things
to do than that.
Raargh!
Oh, I guess you're
all grown up now, huh?
[TSUYOSHI growls] We're goin'
to Mom and Dad's grave site
and tellin' 'em we're
good and Grandpa's good too.
[ISAMI]
Let's go!
[TSUYOSHI] Aww, c'mon.
You like this! Ha ha!
[KOORIYAMA] Uchida, don't
you think we shoulda gone
somewhere a little more
classy for our date?
It's more cooler in
here than it is outside.
[KOORIYAMA]
So, what d'you wanna do,
since we've been
ordered to stay home?
[UCHIDA] I kept going over
it in my head last night.
[KOORIYAMA]
And? What're you thinkin'?
[UCHIDA]
I'm now convinced
the Magic Circle Project
should be called off.
And what would that
accomplish anyway?
Doesn't Shinohara call
all the shots at Ab-Com?
There are other possibilites.
I need to get in contact
with Dr. Mayuzumi.
Who the hell is he?
Dr. Mayuzumi used to be the
Magic Circle Project leader,
but he decided to
resign six months ago.
Resigned?
I have a feelin' that he sensed
the danger of this project
and decided to walk away.
I'll never be absolutely sure
until I see him
and ask him myself.
So tell me, where exactly
is the good doctor
hiding out these days?
Unfortunately, nobody's heard
from him since he resigned.
I think he must have cut some
kind of deal with Shinohara.
And you really think someone
like that is gonna help us out?
Actually, I discovered
somethin' quite interestin'.
Yeah? What did ya find out?
After her parents divorced,
Haruka used her mother's
name instead of her father's.
Wait a minute!
Don't tell me her father's
last name is Mayuzumi?!
You hit the nail on the head.
So he's her father?
[UCHIDA] Yep! And he
goes to visit his daughter
every three months.
If he has any idea of
this project's risk factor,
I am positive that he would
come see his daughter.
[KUINA] Kosagi, I confirmed
your behavioral data.
You disobeyed orders
and attempted to destroy
the Dragon Torque.
By policy your actions would
merit severe punishment,
but we don't have have
time for that right now.
[KOSAGI gasps]
The moment that
Fukuro jumps into action,
we have to secure the Dragon
Torque without fail this time.
It shouldn't be difficult,
if we can eliminate Karasu.
[phone chiming]
[AI]
Seriously?
What in the world does
Miho think she's doing?
She's always late!
Don't mess with me.
[phone buttons beeping
The little priss takes so long,
because she's spending
so much time primping.
[cat yowls]
Uh... Huh?
Uhh...
Huh?
Hey, this is kinda weird
seeing you here like this.
Can I help you, sir?
I don't think I'm old
enough to be a "sir."
Hey, ease up on
Isami a little, will ya?
Huh?
He's just a little kid.
Don't be so tough
on him, all right?
It must be hard to believe,
see me grown up like this.
Who... are you?
[cat yowls]
[AI sighs]
[AI gasps]
He just disappeared.
Karasu. Huh?
Huh? Are you okay?
[ISAMI]
Dude!
Damn bookworm!
You do everything
your momma says.
No, I don't!
Yeah, like hell you don't!
[YU]
I made that decision by myself!
Huh?!
Thanks for worrying
about me. I mean it.
I'm not worrying.
[YU]
It was my call.
I've always done everything
my mom told me to.
[YU] But this is the first
time I've done something,
'cause I wanted to.
[ISAMI]
Good luck with all your exams.
Huh?
We're still friends
no matter where we are.
Ya understand?
Yeah, sure, I gotcha.
You're still the same
guy you were back then,
you know?
Right back at ya, Isami.
[FUKURO]
I ran into Ai.
[FUKURO] Now I know why you're
drawn to this dimension.
[KARASU] I will never
regret coming here...
...and I will protect
Haruka as long as I live.
Hmph...
[FUKURO]
Then it is inevitable.
[KARASU]
I guess so.
[FUKURO] The next time
we meet may be the last...
...my old friend.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[FUKURO]
Stay out of our way.
[ATORI]
I can hear his screams.
[KARASU] I will protect the
Haruka of this dimension.
[HARUKA]
Next episode, "The Battle."
Can't you just stop already?