[KUINA grunting, groaning]
Oh crap, my right arm
didn't make it.
[KUINA]
Isuka, up here.
Kosagi. Tobi.
Kosagi. Status report.
The coordinates that
Atori and Karasu
jumped to are slightly off.
Fukuro can't be confirmed.
[KOSAGI gasps]
Koina, your arm!
[KUINA] Yeah, it's gone.
And my communicator's lost too.
Tobi, put a marker
on this dimension.
[TOBI]
Understood.
[TOBI grunts]
[KUINA]
This dimension is unstable.
[KARASU] You see, there is
nothing at all that you can do
to protect the young lady.
Just who are you?
You see... I am you.
[HARUKA, YU gasp]
[HARUKA] Yu!
[YU groans]
[KARASU]
Ignore him!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
I know you.
I know who you are.
[HARUKA]
This can't be real, can it?
[ATORI] So, apparently the
Dragon Torque is a human.
Atori...
[ATORI cackling]
[ATORI]
I found it first, Karasu.
I found the Dragon Torque.
What? Dragon Torque?
[ATORI]
I'll transport her.
[KARASU]
Wait, Atori!
There's a possibility
the Dragon Torque
can't withstand the
shock of transposition.
[ATORI] I don't need the whole
body. An arm would do nicely.
[ATORI] I'll just take
a piece of her back with me.
[HARUKA gasps]
[ATORI gasps]
I don't think
that's a good idea.
[ATORI] Are you planning to
monopolize all the glory again?
[KARASU] Don't act on
your own until we can
establish communication
with Kuina.
[ATORI grunts]
[ATORI yells]
KARASU grunts]
[ATORI yelling]
Entropic phenomenon
is increasing.
The dimension
is starting to waver.
[KUINA]
What's the cause?
[KOSAGI]
I believe it's the effects
from the stimulant reaction
of the hyperspin.
[KUINA]
Spin weaponry was deployed
in this dimensional world?
[KOSAGI]
We have to stop it now, Kuina,
or a matter violation
will occur.
[KOSAGI gasps]
[KOSAGI] The flow of time
is starting to decelerate.
[HARUKA]
What's that?
[KOSAGI] Time... as we
know it... has stopped.
[ATORI]
Hell.
[KARASU]
You have to stop.
A dimensional resonance
phenomenon is occurring.
[ATORI]
Heh. Karasu... I detest you.
Or maybe you didn't know that.
If you were to simply disappear,
all I would have to say is that
you were flung somewhere
in time and space during combat,
and no one would be
the wiser... I'm sure.
Get it?
Ah!
[HARUKA] What is it about him
that feels so familiar?
[ATORI grunts]
[ATORI, KARASU grunting]
I won't hold back this time!
What are you two doing?
This isn't the time or the place
for you guys to be fighting.
Hell.
[KARASU]
Fukuro, are you in one piece?
There was an error in
the transposition coordinates.
[FUKURO] So did you locate
the Dragon Torque?
[KARASU]
Mm-hm.
Is that... little girl
the Dragon Torque?
Hold on, it won't stabilize.
We're being recalled.
[KUINA]
Anti-shock protection.
[YU gasps]
[YU]
They're gone!
Haruka!
Where did they go?
Where did they disappear to?
I'm really not sure.
[HARUKA]
He's vanished again.
[FRIENDS]
Haruka! Hey, where are you!
Hey, Haruka!
[FRIENDS]
Are you guys okay?
[ISAMI]
Where are you?
[AI]
Thank goodness.
Are you okay?
Nothing happened, right?
Where's the ghost?
Did you see the spirit world?
Miho, you keep quiet, would you?
[MIHO]
Oh... how come?
[AI] Because you'll
confuse everything.
[MIHO]
But that was a ghost, wasn't it?
Oh man. Wow, she's a dweeb.
[AI]
Knock it off!
Hey, Yu... did something
happen out there?
[ISAMI]
Yu!
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Don't worry about it.
[OPERATOR]
Unit stationing complete.
Looks like... we made it back.
[KOSAGI]
Kuina!
[DRAGON WARRIOR]
Are you alright?
[OPERATOR]
One of the units is damaged
Requesting a medical team.
[VOICE 1] The bird's
dimensional transposition
doesn't seem to stabilize.
[VOICE 2] The probability
of success is increasing.
There's no need to worry.
[VOICE 3] However, there are
only seven birds left now.
[VOICE 2] It is possible to
secure the Dragon Torque
with only one bird.
Besides, birds who actually saw
the Dragon Torque survived.
[VOICE 3]
The Dragon Torque exists
in a stabilized dimension.
[VOICE 2]
Its existence is definite.
There is no mistake.
[VOICE 1] If we can obtain
the Dragon Torque,
we can prevent Shangri-la from
corroding our civilization.
[VOICE 3] Can the Dragon
Torque really be captured?
[VOICE 2] If we fail,
then our world, La'cryma,
will cease to exist.
[FUKURO] That dimension exists
15 years ago on the time axis.
Apparently that world is...
...very similar to
our past, my friend.
[FUKURO] The dimension...
where you and I
and she exist together.
It's ironic.
[KARASU] All we have to do
is fulfill our roles:
Stabilize the dimension
under the order of Reizu.
That's our duty
as Dragon Knights.
[FUKURO]
Enough, Karasu!
We will never be controlled
by anybody ever again.
I don't need the responsibility.
Then what's the point?
Why do it?
My friend... good question.
Maybe I just want
to dream again...
...like I did in the old days.
[HARUKA]
What was all that?
Am I going crazy?
[HARUKA] Still... I wasn't
dreaming. It was real.
[chair scuffs]
[MIYUKI]
Hm?
Yu?
[YU]
I'm done.
[door creaks]
[AI]
Hey, wait up, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
No way! I'll be late!
What are ya talkin' about?
It's your own fault
for sleeping in!
I know that,
but I'm gonna be late!
[AI] Alright! So wait up!
[HARUKA] No can do!
[AI] For crying out loud.
You're as fast as a dog.
[HARUKA] I'm not a dog!
[AI] I know that.
You okay, Ai? What's the matter?
[AI gasping, panting]
No... I might die.
[AI]
I'm dead.
Oh, hey, don't damage it.
That's my car.
[AI]
Sorry about that, Miss Yukie.
[MIHO]
Uh-oh, the roof is dented.
[YUKIE]
No way!
A ghost? I gotta tell you girls,
that's really amazing.
You don't believe us! Do you?
[YUKIE]
Of course I believe you!
[HARUKA] You shouldn't talk
with your mouth full.
That was definitely
the real thing.
We finally saw one! Right?
Yeah. That's right.
Isami was really freaking out
about it grabbing his leg.
Impossible.
Oh? I don't think
it's a good idea
for you all to go out
at night by yourselves.
Don't you worry about us.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, 'cause we're fast runners.
That's not the point, Haruka!
She's right. But now
that you mention it,
I heard something similar.
[AI] Are you kidding?
[MIHO] Really?
Miss Yukie, please tell me!
Alright. Apparently,
my mother heard it
from a lady in
the neighborhood...
[YUKIE]
One appeared in Hachibanzaka.
It was an evil spooky spirit
with one arm gone!
Only one arm?
That's similar to the one
that we saw last night!
Amazing! The town is
overflowing with ghosts!
[MIHO] Wow, that means
there's a chance...
Hey you guys.
[MIHO]
I can't wait!
I want you to go straight
to cram school today.
[YU]
I know.
I know you can be accepted
by the university.
[MIYUKI] It's okay. You're smart
enough to get into Tokyo Uni--
Don't even say that.
[MIYUKI gasps]
I don't wanna do any exams.
I won't go to Tokyo.
I'll decide my
own future, understand?
What are you tallking about?
You can still
decide your future.
You really cannot
do it. You can't.
Yu, listen.
I'm the one who knows
what's best for you, and--
No!
[MIYUKI gasps]
[YU grunting yelling]
[door slams]
Hello, Yu.
[ISAMI] Yu! Hey, wait up!
What's with the sleeping bag?
You goin' camping?
You're not running away
from home, are you?
Yeah, as if.
It's for study camp, right?
Man, how lame is that.
You're gonna wear a
victory headband all day.
I will do homework!
I'll pass my classes!
[chanting]
Study! Success! Study! Success!
I don't...
[ISAMI] When are you gonna
quit that cram school, man?
You're really going to
have a breakdown
if you don't cut it out.
[ISAMI] Let's start playing
soccer together again.
You were on the team
last year. What happened?
[YU] I'm not...I'm not nearly
as good a soccer player as you.
You don't have to take
everything so seriously.
Just enjoy it, that's all.
Have some fun.
You wouldn't understand anyway!
Hey, hold on there!
[YU]
Just shut up!
Why, you!
[YU grunting]
Do you do everything
your mother says?
Quit being a wuss!
You're wrong! I'm not
like that. Get off!
Oh yeah, then tell me I'm wrong!
[YU] Someone like you...
[AI] Look, it's Yu and Isami.
It's Yu!
[HARUKA]
Hey you guys, knock it off.
[AI]
Stop it. What are you doing?
Cut it out, Isami!
You okay?
Damn! What is wrong with you?
[AI]
Isami...
[AI groans]
That boy has a problem.
[HARUKA] That backpack... are
you running way from home, Yu?
Hey, don't follow me.
But we promised that we
would run away together.
You certainly don't
have any reason
to run away from home!
[YU] Sure, maybe your dad
doesn't live with you,
but your mother
trusts you, doesn't she?
Your father cares
about you, doesn't he?
You don't know
how lucky you are.
It's different in my house.
It's all fallen apart.
[YU] Even when it comes to my
well-being... she talks like
she cares, but she doesn't
actually care inside.
[HARUKA]
You know that's not true.
Yes it is. You know
I'm telling the truth.
[HARUKA]
Let me come with you.
Huh?
We made a promise.
Don't you remember?
To run away
from home together...
What do you say? We can go
anywhere you wanna go.
[YU]
What are we doing here anyway?
[HARUKA] After all,
if we're running away,
we won't be coming
back for a while.
So let's enjoy this
last look at the city.
Be careful, Yoshi!
Okay!
Hey Mommy, over here!
[YOSHI]
Come on, hurry!
It's really high up!
You could almost touch
the clouds. You should see it.
[MOM]
Really?
[YOSHI]
Yeah! The cars look like ants.
[MOM]
Really? I wanna see too.
[YOSHI]
Okay.
[YU]
One last look, huh?
[HARUKA] It looks like
the coast is clear.
[YU]
Now what?
Let's stay right here tonight.
[YU]
What? Stay here?
Why not? We have
no other place to go.
Yeah, but still...
[HARUKA] You know... I'm gonna
borrow your sleeping bag.
I'm feeling kinda tired.
You're crazy.
[YU] What happened yesterday
wasn't a dream, right?
You saw him too.
Well didn't you?
He wasn't an hallucination.
And he wasn't a ghost.
Yu...
He mocked me. He said
I couldn't do anything.
I can't get that out of my head!
You really can't
do it. You can't.
Yu...
[HARUKA gasps]
[murmuring]
[YU]
Do you hear that?
Someone... someone's here.
Yu!
Can you hear that?
What... What is that?
What the hell is that?
[YU whimpers]
What's going on?
This can't be right.
[HARUKA]
You see them too?
Yeah. I see lots
of people everywhere.
[YOSHI]
Hurry up!
That's the boy we saw
when we were here earlier.
[YOSHI]
Hey Mommy, over here!
It can't... It can't be real.
We're seeing some
kind of optical illusion.
[SCARY VOICE] That is neither
a mirage nor an illusion.
It is dimensional resonance.
[HARUKA]
Who's there?
[SCARY VOICE] The past and
the future have not separated.
Similar to an Uroboros.
What's that?
What was that you said, Haruka?
[SCARY VOICE] The beginning
passes from the ending
to once again be the beginning.
[SCARY VOICE]
To find the one who will become
the absolute observer
in order to exist...
What'd you say?
I can't hear you now!
[HARUKA]
Yu...
[HARUKA gasps]
[ISUKA grunting]
Are you alright, Tobi?
Or did you get hurt?
[TOBI]
I'm okay.
Were the site
coordinates off again?
[ATORI cackling]
I am in luck.
I am the closest one to her.
[ATORI]
I'll get the Dragon Torque.
[ATORI cackles]
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again.
That summer day's dream...
Don't! Please, stop!
I can't! I can't do it!
[ATORI]
I won't let you go.
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "Hunted."
Someone... save me.