[HARUKA] At that time,
I was blanketed in light.
I suddenly became
a part of that light,
tumbling to a distant horizon.
[HARUKA] And someone was
sharing my aurora space.
I soared to a land
beyond all dimensions.
[HARUKA]
Who is that?
Where are we?
[HARUKA gasps]
[DRAGON KNIGHTS]
Let the Dragon sleep.
[KARASU gasps]
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
What's wrong?!
It's the Dragon Knights.
Dragon Knights?
[DRAGON KNIGHTS]
Let the Dragon sleep.
This dimension's
called La'cryma.
It is very different
from your world.
[DRAGON KNIGHTS]
Let the Dragon sleep.
La'cryma?
[DRAGON KNIGHTS]
Let the Dragon sleep.
Never! I won't surrender Haruka!
Take her!
[DRAGON KNIGHTS] Let the Dragon
sleep. Let the Dragon sleep.
Let the Dragon sleep.
I can't hold on--!
[DRAGON KNIGHTS]
Let the Dragon sleep.
Ah, Karasu!
[HARUKA gasps]
[ENRA] I am assuming the
Dragon Torque is secured?
[GOKAN] We certainly did not
expect that child's body
to have accumulated that many
Reizu sub-atomic particles.
[TAIZA] It is impossible
to fully predict
different dimensions.
[ENRA] The invasion of
Shangri-la is not logical.
[GOKAN]
That's just an excuse.
[TAIZA] They distort dimensions
like attacking savages.
[TAIZA] At any rate,
we can now prevent
Shangri-la from destroying us.
[GOKAN] If we could
incorporate the Dragon Torque
into the Reizu simulator--
[TAIZA]
That is only a hypothesis.
[ENRA]
I believe...
...we must see this experiment
through to the end...
[GOKAN]
...to see the significance
of mankind's existence...
So, will we be...
absolutely recognized
by the observer of the universe?
Or...?
[YU] She disappeared...
right before my eyes...
This bright light suddenly
appeared all around her...
Yu!
She disappeared from
right in front of us, too.
Remember, guys?
Okay, so was she really with
a guy in a black cape or not?
He took her away,
can't you hear?!
Yu...
Pull yourself together, Yu!
Did she really disappear?!
Or was she taken by somebody?!
It's...
It's all my fault...!
Hey... You know that
it's not your fault.
We should go see if
we can find her.
Yeah, you're right.
Perhaps we should
talk to Ms. Yukie.
[AI] With Ms. Yukie?
Do you think she'll believe us?
Oh, why not?! Yeah,
let's call up Ms. Yukie!
We haven't seen her since
summer vacation began!
Why are you so excited?
Hey, could you at least pretend
to be worried about Haruka?
[ISAMI] Of course I'm worried!
What're you talking about?!
I'm very worried!
You're acting like such a spaz.
You are a horny toad!
Miho, what did you call me?!
[MIHO] You boys are
like a cat in heat!
[UCHIDA]
Huh?
It's that boy.
[MIHO] Here, kitty-kitty!
[ISAMI] That's impossible!
[AI] I think you're just
using Haruka as an excuse
to see Ms. Yukie!
You know she's right.
[ISAMI]
I am not! Take it back!!
[UCHIDA] Yu! Yu! Will you
please look at this picture?!
[AI]
Haruka?!
Do you know where
Haruka is right now?
Why do you wanna know?
[UCHIDA] If you know
anything, please, tell me.
[YU]
She's gone.
She's what?
Then it's possible
we're too late.
[UCHIDA]
If she moved through dimensions
surrounded by the
foam of Wheeler...
[YU] What does that mean?
What's gonna happen to her?
Well, it may not be possible
for her to return to this world.
[HARUKA gasps]
Where am I?
What is this place?
Hey... What...
What're you doing?
Hey, knock it off!
[WOMAN 1]
Blood pressure, 107 over 66.
Respiration 14, pulse rate 82.
[WOMAN 3]
Body temperature is 36.7.
[WOMAN 1]
All vital signs are normal.
Her readings are stable,
Lady Amamiku.
Don't you know it's against
the law to kidnap people?!
You were brought
here to La'cryma
from a dimension that
still exists in the past.
The past?
According to your perspective,
this world is in the future.
Future? What're you
talking about? Where am I?
[AMAMIKU] La'cryma. This is
what we call this dimension.
[HARUKA] Hmmm...
He said the same thing...
Tell me, what'd you
do with Karasu?
Well, if you must know...
[KUINA] I didn't expect
you to sink this low.
I prevented the monastic
order from disposing of you.
Haruka...
Open your eyes, will ya?!
No matter how much it
may resemble your past,
it is not our world!
Can't you understand that?!
You're wrong...
I'm not! Don't confuse things!
You will not kill Haruka.
But aren't you responsible
for Isuka's death?
[KARASU]
Yes I am, that's right...
[KUINA]
We also lost Tobi and Atori.
They betrayed us to
remain in that dimension.
[KARASU]
Betrayed...?
You're going to have to give me
all of your strength, Karasu.
[KUINA] You should know
that this dimension
is different from our past.
In order to establish
our existence...
we were granted the power.
[YUKIE]
If you're... wait a minute!
You're Ms. Uchida, right?
[UCHIDA]
Yes, it is.
I've mentioned this
several times, but...
the children have also witnessed
the same phenomenon that we did.
I guess Mr. Kooriyama's badge
and I.D. are legitimate...
But what is a policeman like him
doing with a
scientist like you?!
I am not going to explain myself
to a simple-minded
schoolteacher like you!
Hey, who in the hell are
you calling simple-minded?!
Ms. Yukie, please don't
start fighting!
[KOORIYAMA] C'mon, calm down.
Come on ladies,
let's not start a catfight.
[BOTH]
Piss off!
It's-It's so horrifying!
[AMAMIKU]
It's dinnertime.
[HARUKA]
Ah... okay...
Ugh!
[HARUKA]
Is this even edible?
It is.
[HARUKA]
Uck...
Ewww...
Y'know, this really
is kinda tasty.
Is this actually the future?
Because if this really
is the future,
don't you think you're
sort of changing the past
by bringing me to this place?
[AMAMIKU]
It won't affect our dimension.
Why not?
You see, all of the dimensions
diverge into infinity.
[HARUKA]
I don't understand.
[AMAMIKU] Every dimension
in which you exist
continues on throughout
time to infinity.
You see, even if you were to
remain here for all eternity,
you would only disappear
from the dimension
from which you came. But,
in all the other dimensions,
you would continue to exist.
That is why dimensions continue
to flow from past to future.
So, since I'm gone
from my world...
...nothing is going to change?
Not entirely. We are all hoping
that by you being here...
...it will be possible
to change our future.
[ATORI]
Tobi, I feel very weak.
[TOBI] What do you expect?
We released our pipelines.
[ATORI]
Huh?
[TOBI] Since we took
ourselves off the pipeline,
La'cryma won't be able
to secure our positions...
And they won't
be able to send us
the existence-prolonging data.
And that's why we're going
to continue to have trouble
stabilizing our existence
in this dimension.
[ATORI]
Damn...
[TOBI]
That's not the worst of it.
Because we are unstable,
we could eventually disappear.
[ATORI]
How long do we have?
[TOBI]
I don't know. Even I can't tell.
[ATORI]
You're useless!
But... I wonder if it would
really be all that bad?
What do you mean?
[TOBI] If I had to choose a
world in which to disappear,
this quiet place
wouldn't be so bad.
[ATORI]
Don't be stupid!
I haven't even started
fighting yet, ya hear?!
Bring 'em on!
I'll destroy them all!
Before I'm finished,
I'll destroy... everything!
[HARUKA]
Excuse me, who is she?
Did you call her "Amamicoo"?
Excuse me, I'm talking to you...
[dishes clatter]
Huh?
[HARUKA]
It hurts!
[WOMAN 1]
What's wrong?!
What are you doing?!
Stop!
Someone stop her!
Open up the door!
Huh?!
[HARUKA panting]
[HARUKA] This crazy place
isn't the future!
They think I'm just a kid and
that I'll believe anything!
Where do I go now?
[HARUKA]
Huh...?
I wonder what this room's for...
[HARUKA gasps]
You don't look familiar to me.
[HARUKA]
Well, actually, I'm new here.
Huh? I see... You sure we
haven't met somewhere before?
No, no!
[HARUKA]
You look just like Miho...
My name is Lily!
Miho is my mother!
Who are you anyway, stranger?
Who, who, who?!
[OLD MAN]
Raaaauuggghhh...
The clouds are moving...
Storms building...
Rain will pour down on us!
The rain's coming!
Rain! Rain! It will rain!
It will rain!
Well, I guess it
looks like you're not
the only weirdo
around here anymore.
Hey... Do you know where
I can get a drink of water?
I'm feeling kinda thirsty.
Is that a joke?!
Water is very hard to come by!
[WOMAN 1]
I'm truly sorry, Lady Amamiku.
[GOKAN]
Amamiku.
You were given one order,
you will complete it.
The responsiblities you were
given have to be fulfilled.
[AMAMIKU]
I am aware of that.
Bring her back right away.
You cannot fail again.
[AMAMIKU]
I understand.
It's imperative that
we do not alter
the initiation sequencing
for the Dragon Torque.
Do you understand?
Yes.
[FUKURO]
I'm surprised she got away.
She couldn't have gotten
very far on her own.
You're sure?
Were you surprised... at what
Dragon Torque looked like?
Karasu is very confused.
And you?
Well, let's see... I don't know.
It's all rather confusing.
To me, La'cryma is the only
reality that truly exists.
I see. But I want to be the one
to bring the
Dragon Torque back here.
If I don't do something, I'll be
banished to the upper strata.
[FUKURO]
Oh, all right.
I promise to contact you as soon
as I discover her whereabouts.
[AMAMIKU] I'm sorry. I know...
I'm being a real pain.
No, it's okay. Don't worry,
it'll all work out.
I'll be in touch.
Ah!
Hey, you said this place
is underground, right?
[LILY]
Yes, duh!
[HARUKA] Okay. So, do you
know how to get above ground?
[LILY]
You're kidding, right?
You have a death wish
or somethin'?
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Don't you know that there
are monsters above ground?!
Monsters?
That's right? When the
Uroboros appears in the sky,
the monsters come
to swallow our world!
[LILY]
It's the Dragon Knights...
They don't usually come
all the way down here...
Hey, Lily. I know you
may think I'm crazy,
but... you have to tell me
how to get above ground.
[LILY]
For real?
Yes.
You're really dumb.
How come?
I mean, you can't use
a transporter, right?
Because you probably
don't even have one.
What's a transporter?
You are so annoying!
Become Reizu!
Whatever. I just don't get it.
But there must be another
way you've heard about?
[LILY]
Huh?
Come to think of it...
That crazy old guy did mention
something to me once...
Tell me! Tell me what it was!
[LILY]
Huh?
[LILY screams]
Don't look down, whoa!
[LILY] Why do I have
to come with you?!
[HARUKA] You wanted to come!
You said it sounded fun!
[LILY] I take it back!
I'm going back!
[HARUKA] Lily, it's too
late to go back now!
[LILY sobbing]
[HARUKA]
Crying will make you fall down!
Just show some guts, will ya?!
Mama, please help me!
[WOMAN gasps]
[DRAGON KNIGHT] The crazy
old man said he saw someone
resembling the Dragon Torque
near the ventilation duct.
[FUKURO]
Huh?!
That's above ground!
This is the surface...?
I think so...
[HARUKA]
But there's nothing here.
[LILY]
Haruka, where're you going?!
It's dangerous out there!
What happened to this place...?
Ah?
[HARUKA gasps]
[AMAMIKU]
Wait!
Don't bother trying to run.
There is nothing
for you to find here.
Where am I?! What am I doing
in this place anyway?!
[AMAMIKU] I'm sure you
have already realized
that for yourself.
[HARUKA]
It can't be...
[AMAMIKU]
It's true.
Now you know that
this world is the future.
[HARUKA]
This can't be true.
Liar!
I'm your friend. Ai.
[HARUKA gasps]
Ai Amamiku Hasebe.
You can't be... Ai...
No way...
No, that can't be right!
You're too old to be Ai!
It's 15 years in the future
from your timeline.
It's 15 years?
This is our future?
[HARUKA] Why does the future
of the world look like this?
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[KOSAGI]
Haruka is dead!
[HARUKA]
Will I ever see anybody again?
[YU]
I have to find Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Next, "Precious Person."
Tell me the truth.