[ATORI]
Tobi, begin the process.
[TOBI]
Okay, but we have to hurry.
Coordinates set.
Begin countdown.
[TOBI]
Done. Atori, we're ready to go.
So be it. Now we say
goodbye to La'cryma.
I guess this is farewell...
You're right. So true.
[HARUKA] Baron! Watch the
house while I'm gone, okay?
[BARON barks]
[HARUKA]
I'm seeing things...
Hi!
[MIHO]
You're late!
[MIHO'S MOM]
Come in, come in!
Haruka, Ai, what's wrong?
Mrs. Mukai, what's with
the glasses?!
Aren't they great?
These are the Aura Glasses
I ordered a few days ago!
I see a red aura around Ai, Mom!
Are you certain? I'm pretty sure
I'm seeing a blue
light around her.
[AI]
You're imagining things.
It's definitely there,
you just have to concentrate.
[MIHO &amp; MIHO'S MOM]
Show us!
Well, that certainly proves it.
This family's nuts.
Hey, Mom, Haruka has been
telling us some really
mysterious things have been
happening around her recently,
so I'm determined to find out
the actual cause of her visions.
Let me think how...
Ah, you should probably
use the Prophecy Board
I bought the other day!
Oh! Great idea!
Maybe we should leave...
Impossible. She's doing
this for my benefit.
I want nothing to do with
the UFO summoning ceremony.
[BARON whines]
[MIHO]
This is a Prophecy Board.
We ask it whatever
questions we have,
and the spirits give us answers!
Oh...
It's come down to this, has it?
Haruka, put your
hand right here.
Um, sure.
[MIHO]
Now, gather all your senses
and focus them on your
questions, then wish
ever-so gently so as not to
startle the spirits of the dead
who inhabit the Ouija board.
Spirits of the dead... Right...
[MIHO] Spirits, Haruka
is presently distressed
about recent
mysterious events...
If you please, inform us
of their purpose.
Uh-huh.
[MIHO]
Hey, Ai!
Since you're here, you have
to do the chant with us!
What?! I have to do it, too?!
Yes, we do it all together now.
Oh, Spirits, hear us,
oh, Spirits.
[ALL]
Haruka is presently distressed
about recent mysterious events.
If it pleases you, inform us
of their purpose.
Oh, Spirits. Spirits hear us...
It moved!
No way!
[AI]
N...
[MIHO]
O...
[AI]
E...
[MIHO]
I...
[HARUKA]
Another N!
"Noein"... I guess?
[MIHO]
Yeah, but what does it mean?
Beats me.
Me, too. It makes
no sense at all.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess we can
forget about me now.
Since that's over, why don't
we ask the Ouija board
Something more interesting?
More interesting...
Oh, hey, I know!
Let's ask it when
Miho's gonna get hitched!
What?! No!
[MIHO giggling]
No, no! You can't ask that! It's
too embarrassing! Please, don't!
Aren't we supposed to use
it to tell our fortunes?
Yes, but marriage of all
things... We can't do that.
Miho, you're starting to sweat.
Are you hot or something?
[MIHO]
It is kinda warm.
[KUINA] Have they
ascertained the coordinates
of Atori and the others?
[FUKURO]
No, apparently not yet.
[KUINA]
What are the observers doing?
[FUKURO]
You can't blame them.
Ever since one of the
investigators was killed,
they've become desperate.
They've tarnished our good name.
[FUKURO] Atori is going after
the Dragon Torque.
We should find them
and its coordinates.
[KOSAGI]
How critical is the situation?
It's bad!
[FUKURO]
I'll go in ahead of you,
search for Atori with Karasu.
[KUINA]
Dammit! Everything is in chaos.
[HARUKA]
Thanks for having us over!
[AI]
Bye, Miho!
[HARUKA]
Bye.
[MIHO]
Bye!
Such nice girls.
Of course they are, Mom.
I choose my friends wisely.
[FUKURO]
Is this nostalgic for you?
The Haruka in this dimension
is not the Haruka
we know from ours.
I know.
She must be sacrificed
so we... can continue.
It makes you think...
Everything that occurs
here is the beginning
of everything
that is to come.
[KARASU]
What happened?
[FUKURO] Atori and the others
transported here on their own.
We can't lock on them;
their coordinates are unstable.
Atori and the others?
Be careful, Karasu.
[KARASU]
Understood.
[KOORIYAMA] You're workin'
really hard, Uchida.
You wanna beer? Why don't you
just relax for a little while?
Get a little rest.
Kooriyama, we've already
finished tomorrow's schedule,
so would you please
get out of here
and go back to your own room?
I don't really have
time to take a break
because I need to have all of
this data organized by tomorrow.
It sounds like a lot of work.
Hey, Kooriyama, don't those
holes in the brick...
...make you wonder
just a little bit?
This kinda stuff
is your specialty.
After all, you're
the Ab-Com genius.
So I'm gonna leave it to you.
Kooriyama, would you please
do me a favor and not use
that awful abbreviation?!
Call it by it's full name:
The Absolute Critical Prevention
Strategy Committee.
Gotcha!
So... How're your abs doin'?
Have you heard of
"sexual harassment?"
[YU gasps]
[MIYUKI sighs]
[MIYUKI] Look at the time.
I need to start
getting supper ready. Do you
want something to eat?
Hamburger? Would you
like some stew?
No thanks. S'okay...
I am your mother, so I
know what's best for you!
[MIYUKI]
Please, Yu. Do what I'm asking.
I beg of you, don't betray me.
You're a good boy, aren't you?
I really believe in you, Son.
You won't disappoint me.
I know in my heart you can
be just like my sister...
[phone ringing]
[ISAMI sighs]
What d'ya think you're doing?!
Quit screwing around
and keep practicing!
Shut up. I happen to be
visualizing the game in my head.
Oh yeah?
I really don't think I could
take it... if I were him.
Did you try calling him
on his cell phone?
I did, but his mom took it
away from him. Like, eons ago.
[AI]
Oh...
Like getting into
that stupid school
is gonna do anything
for him anyway.
Just because you go
to a great school
doesn't mean you're gonna
have a perfect life.
Right, Ai?
That's just your lame excuse
because you hate
studying so much.
It is not! I'm worried about Yu!
Alright. Whatever.
Hey, just what the heck do
you think you're doin', Ai?!
Oh, suck it up!
Okay, crazy chick!
[KIDS laughing]
What are you so pissed about?
...Moron.
That girl has lost it.
Oh, Yu... What is so upsetting?
It didn't hurt at all, Tobi.
We don't know
about the pipeline.
Or what the effects
of releasing it will be.
I'm starting to like it here.
The sky is blue. I would be very
happy to disappear here forever.
Isuka!
[ATORI]
I won't disappear that easily.
Not until I destroy
the Dragon Torque.
I'm tellin' ya,
that lady's impossible!
What do you mean?
So, I decided to go over
to Yu's house and say hi.
[ISAMI] "Yu is studying
and can not play."
She's, like, totally gone
off the deep end.
[MIHO]
It can't be helped because
he's studying for his exams.
She does have a point.
Yeah, but this is gonna be our
last summer break to hang out.
I mean, if he qualifies,
he'll be going off to Tokyo
and I'll be stuck
here by myself.
I guess he really is
going to go off, huh?
Hey, do you guys know
if Yu even wants
to go to a middle
school in Tokyo?
How am I supposed to know?!
I can't even talk to him!
Ah! Wait, I'll just
crawl through
his window tonight and ask him.
Mine's open.
[AI]
Hey!
Knock it off.
Ugh! That hurt, Ai.
Don't be so obvious.
[TIME DRIFTER]
Young lady...
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Be careful of your actions.
You are causing vacillation.
Is he talking to me...?
Haruka, what's wrong?
That guy's talking to me!
What guy? Where is he?
What do you mean "what guy"?
He's right over... there...
There's nobody there...
Who're you talking about?
[HARUKA]
Nobody else can see him...
[TOBI]
Coordinates locked.
5... 4... 3... 2...
No! It will cause a rift!
Time will tear!
[HARUKA gasps]
I've got her!
Ai, help me!
Haruka!
You damn fool, Atori!
You ripped time!
[AI]
Haruka...?
Haruka disappeared...
Definitely the strongest
reading we've ever gotten.
[UCHIDA]
Keep going straight.
I told you to go straight.
[KOORIYAMA] Take it easy.
The road has a bend in it.
Huh?
That was painful...
[HARUKA] How'd I get
all the way over here...?
[HARUKA gasps]
[ATORI cackles] Illusion...
It's just an illusion...
Dragon Torque!
Tobi, release the Reizu
of the Dragon Torque.
Tobi, what's wrong
with you? Get up.
She has used too much power.
Damn.
Too bad, Isuka.
Never mind. You do it.
[ISUKA]
So you're certain
that if we destroy
the Dragon Torque--
[ATORI]
Just do it.
Karasu!
What do you intend to do
with the Dragon Torque?
You again... How annoying.
Karasu! You don't understand!
It's too dangerous!
If we return to La'cryma
with the Dragon Torque,
the entire dimension
could be blown away!
"Risk", huh...?
Did you say "risk"?!
[KARASU] Don't make me laugh!
It is too late for us!
We live this quantum
existence in which
all order has been destroyed!
La'cryma is no longer
what it was!
If it is true that
the Dragon Torque
will actually obliterate
all existing dimensions...
...then so be it!
So like you, Karasu.
Wanting a fight.
I don't see any other choice!
We shall destroy him together!
[ATORI cackles]
[ATORI]
Die, scum!
[ISUKA yells]
[KARASU grunts]
[KARASU groans]
Ugh. He wreaks havoc again!
Atori, you damn fool!
[ISUKA grunts]
Impressive, Karasu!
[HARUKA screams]
Let me go!
No, don't!
[ATORI] Isuka, hurry up and
destroy the Dragon Torque.
Help! Let go of me!
Give it up now, Karasu!
Release her!
Do it, kill her now, Isuka!
Yu...
Haruka?!
[KARASU]
Haruka will eventually...
...disappear from your sight.
[KARASU]
Don't! Stop it! Isuka!
Help... me...!
[KARASU]
Stop!
[KARASU sputters]
[ISUKA gasps]
[KARASU yells]
[HARUKA groans]
[ISUKA groans]
[KARASU yells]
Sure is a nice day.
Hey, these readings are
definitely on the rise again.
Let's head over this way.
Okay...
Damn, Karasu triggered
a high-side!
We're not prepared for that...
[ATORI]
Tobi... I'd forgotten about you.
[KARASU growls]
Karasu... This is farewell...
At least now I'll be
out of misery...
[KARASU gasps]
Blue snow...
[HARUKA]
Karasu...
Goodbye, Karasu...
[KARASU moaning, yelling]
[HARUKA gasps]
Go! Hell calls you!
[HARUKA]
Stop it!
Please, don't destroy my home!
It would make... It would
make everyone sad.
[HARUKA]
Please stop!
[HARUKA gasps]
[NOEIN]
Haruka...
Think of the future...
The future you wish for...
You have the power
to make it so...
Envision it... Believe it...
What's this?!
[KARASU] Did she substitute it
with a different dimension?
Does this Haruka have the power
to manipulate dimensions?!
[KARASU gasps]
[HARUKA]
I feel weak...
What happened...?
What happened to me...?
Karasu, are you hurt?!
[KARASU]
No.
Wait a minute...
Is that the Dragon Torque?
You secured it?
I have not.
What in the world was
that unusual power?
Where is Atori?
I killed Isuka during combat.
[FUKURO]
What have you done?!
[KARASU] I cannot surrender
the Dragon Torque!
[FUKURO]
Karasu!
[KARASU]
I will not hand over Haruka.
This is bad...
Karasu, you damn fool...
We must get him, and fast.
Tell me you... saw that...
I saw it I think...
But... do you believe it?
[UCHIDA]
Good point.
[KOORIYAMA]
Did you get a shot of it?
What's this?
[MIYUKI]
Yu? What's wrong? I'm coming in.
[phone ringing]
[YU]
Why won't she answer?
[KARASU] You must protect
this girl with your life...
What are you talking about?
[KOSAGI] I can forcefully
transport Karasu.
Not now, dammit!
Yu...
[HARUKA]
Yu!
[YU]
Haruka!
[YU gasps]
Haruka...
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer's day dream.
[KARASU]
This Earth is La'cryma.
[KUINA]
Get him!
[UCHIDA] She may not be able to
come back to this world again.
It's all my fault.
[HARUKA]
Next, "The Dimension of Tears."
Where is this place?