My mom looks so wonderful!
This is amazing! I can't
wait to get married myself!
[HARUKA]
This really is wonderful.
Your mom makes
a pretty bride, Ai.
I'm sorry, who are you again?
[MIHO]
What's wrong?
[AI]
Miho, do you know this girl?
Hey, who you guys
talkin' to over here?
Isami, do you know who she is?
Um... Hi there, can you
tell me your name again?
I've never seen her before...
Huh? What's going on?
[ISAMI]
Hey, Yu!
[YU]
Huh?
Any idea who this could be?
Hello? It's me!
And who are you again?
No...
Hey, what is it, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Ugh, there she goes,
spacing out again.
[HARUKA]
No... I...
I think I was having a really
bizarre daydream or something.
You can dream while
you're walking?
Yeah, that's our Haruka.
That dream you just had...
Was it a hallucination that
everyone had forgotten you?
But how can you be
completely certain
that you're actually
here right now?
Or... is this dimension
only an illusion?
[NOEIN]
Perhaps you are just lost
in a dream of a
phantom dimension?
[NOEIN]
Think about it... Haruka.
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
Ai's parent's wedding...
It really happened
yesterday, didn't it...?
I was there too, wasn't I...?
Hang on, this whole thing
can't be just a dream, can it?
Oh, wait, I know.
[HARUKA]
Hmm...
Hm.
[HARUKA]
Got it!
I do exist!
I knew it.
I mean, these are of me.
[HARUKA] These are all pictures
of me when I was really little.
[HARUKA]
Huh...?
There's gotta be more.
I don't remember
this video tape, do I?
A magnetic tape?
Haven't seen these in a while.
[HARUKA] I tried to watch it
on my video player,
but it didn't work.
Can you help?
It's probably configured
differently from the tape.
[HARUKA]
Then how can I watch it?
Let me think... Huh...
Is there something
important recorded on it?
I think it just has footage
of me when I was little.
I would like to see that, too!
Can I watch it with you, Haruka?
Of course you can, Atori!
So, Tobi, what should I do?
Well, I think the
quickest way would be
to find a deck that can play
this kind of video tape.
[YU]
This is an 8mm video.
Unfotunately, I don't have
a deck that can play
this kind of tape either.
[HARUKA] Well, do you know
anyone that might have one?
I don't think I do.
It's a pretty outdated format.
So, why do you wanna see
this all of a sudden?
Umm... I don't know... It's
really kind of hard to explain.
But I wanna watch it, okay?!
I just have to see it, please?!
Take it easy!
Why don't we just ask Isami?
Maybe his brother knows where
we might be able to find one.
[KUINA] Damn you! Damn you!
Damn you! Damn you!
Damn you!
[NOEIN]
Betrayed again? How very sad.
[KUINA]
Huh?
[NOEIN] Your destiny
is inevitably unfortunate.
I pity you, Kuina.
Noein! Please! Please,
take me away to Shangri-la!
And do it right away!
[NOEIN]
That I cannot do.
You have yet to fulfill
your part of the negotiation.
It won't be that easy!
The Dragon Torque's
power is increasing!
[NOEIN]
This power has accelerated
thanks to its contact
with La'cryma.
[NOEIN]
More than I had predicted.
[NOEIN] With that much power,
the Dragon Torque
can now come to
Shangri-la on its own will.
I have lost faith in you, Kuina.
And I have come all the way to
La'cryma to grant your request.
No, wait a minute...!
[NOEIN]
You have completed your duty.
This is goodbye, Kuina.
Don't do this, Noein! Please!
Take me there, please!
Take me to Shangri-la!
Please! Please!
Don't leave me here...
[MIHO]
An 8mm video, huh?
It's highly doubtful that anyone
still uses those things today.
That's funny.
I kinda thought there might
be one lying around your house,
since you're so rich
with tons of stuff.
No, no, silly girl.
The rich will constantly
discard anything that is old
in favor of buying
something that is new.
Everyone knows there is only
one thing the rich treasure:
That is cold, hard cash.
Yeah, yeah.
[MIHO] In an emergency,
cash always wins, hands down.
I think that's right.
Haruka!
I have a feeling.
I think this just might
be a cursed video tape!
What?
Like, if you don't
watch it, you'll die!
That's it, isn't it?!
It's a cursed videotape!
If anyone else watches it...
Well, this was a waste of
an hour. Where's Yu looking?
He's at Isami's to see
if he's got one.
He's with Isami?
Ooh! I just knew it! You like
Isami! That's unbelievably cute!
Shut it, Miho!
It's not cute, and I don't
like him, so knock it off!
[MIHO] I think you protest
too much! Heh, heh.
--[AI] Miho!
--[MIHO] Waah!
[KUINA] I swear I will
get to Shangri-la...!
[KOORIYAMA] So you're just
gonna go up and ask her?
Yes, I think it's probably
the quickest way
to get in touch with
Dr. Mayuzumi. You agree?
[KOORIYAMA] I guess,
but don't you think he's gonna
be kinda suspicious if we
get his kid mixed up in this?
[UCHIDA]
She's already mixed up in this.
Haruka may be at the
center of it all.
[KOORIYAMA]
I still don't buy it.
These alternative dimensions
or whatever you call it.
I keep thinking that we're just
having the same long nightmare.
[TOBI]
There you are.
So what are you doing here?
Watching the ocean.
How come?
Because there's not one where I
come from. As far as I remember.
Maybe that's okay.
You should stop
thinking about it
and let all the unpleasant
things stay forgotten.
Yes, I suppose. It's just...
I'm still worried about Sara...
[TOBI]
Atori...
Hi, good afternoon. Would you
know if Haruka is around?
Hi. Actually, I don't think
she's here right now.
Let's wait inside.
You sure?
Do you think I can't sense you?
Why are you following me?
Because I'm watching you.
To keep my promise.
I said I would watch you
vanish in this dimension,
and I meant it.
[KARASU]
Hmph.
Behave yourself until you
synchronize to this dimension.
Karasu!
[KOSAGI gasps]
[KUINA] So you ran off
to be with Karasu.
I never though you
would betray me.
Kuina!
[KUINA]
You care for him so much,
that you decided to disappear
at his side in this dimension.
Don't you understand?!
Every dimension in existance
only gives pain to the living!
Think of your own past!
Wasn't it filled with
darkness and despair?!
Shangri-la is trying
to realign time
and straighten out the warp!
You've sided with Shangri-la?!
If you were to go there,
you'd be free
from all your pain
and suffering!
You traitor!
[KUINA] Use this and survive
as long as possible.
[TOBI] We came to this dimension
to capture the Dragon Torque.
The Dragon Torque?
What the hell is that?
[TOBI] I think I should tell you
everything there is to know.
Dragon Torque is a codename
for the aggregate
of high-density Reizu particles.
Reizu particles?
I don't understand;
what were you trying
to do with them?
You see, our dimension's
on the verge of obliteration.
We came into contact with
one called "Shangri-la"
which caused out
dimension to break down.
The Reizu keeps it together.
Dimensions bein' obliterated...
And you discovered
a way to prevent it?
[TOBI]
Well... sort of... However--
Okay, I think it's a little late
to start keeping
secrets, don't you?
Yes, you're right. We built a
quantum computer in our reality,
and it estimated
the coordinates.
Then Atori and I, as quantized
humans, observed and confirmed
the existance of the Dragon
Torque in the other dimension.
The first one of us to find
the Dragon Torque was Karasu.
Unfortunately, in the process,
he was flung into
the dimensional ravine
in mid-combat.
Hold on a sec, don't tell me
that your Dragon
Torque is really...?
[TOBI] This world is just
a coordinate calculated
by our quantum computer.
It was only supposed
to be imaginary numbers.
The skies, the Earth-- it's all
simply an illusion to us.
And the Dragon Torque was
supposed to be exactly the same.
However...
But the instant you
all transported
into the world of
imaginary numbers,
this dimension became
real to you.
As did our friend Haruka in
the form of a 12 year-old girl.
The problem is,
the reality you came from
is only one of many
possible futures,
and, if whatever happened
to cause that future
in your dimension is
startin' to happen here--
Just a moment, Miss Uchida!
Your future is based on
a computer generating
imaginary numbers.
There is just no way in which
the reality of my world
can be influenced
by this dimension.
That might be, but the
Magic Circle Project
is about to start.
They are runnin' an experiment
which, if successful, will
artifically create the Reizu
particles to which you refer.
[TOBI]
That's bad.
With Shangri-la's erasure
of this dimension,
it is realizing the end
of all causation.
So you're sayin' that our world
is startin' to be influenced
by the future as well?
The ocean...
The ocean is glowing...
[KUINA]
You have impressive agility
despite being severed
from the pipeline.
It's a shame to destroy such
an exemplary Dragon Soldier.
In your current state,
I alone can defeat you.
[KUINA]
Now, die!
Not bad, Karasu!
[KARASU groans]
[KUINA]
Sh... Shangri-la!
[ISAMI]
My brother said he borrowed it
from a friend of his.
[AI] Aren't you glad you found
a video player, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
Uh-huh.
[MIHO]
Now we can find out the truth
behind the cursed videotape!
Will you knock it off?
Let's all go watch
it at my place!
Like she wants us to watch those
embarassing videos with her.
It's not that
they're embarassing...
I think if it's a
bunch of memories,
then maybe you should
watch it by yourself.
[NOEIN]
Haruka...
Who is that?
[NOEIN]
I'm coming for you...
Hey, what's the matter, Haruka?
I don't think I
like this wind...
[HARUKA]
Something's coming...
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
There it is.
Shangri-la...
Not Destructrons...!
Kuina!
Hey, what could
that thing be, guys?
Doesn't look like
a plane, does it?
I don't think so! Pretty sure
it's something else!
[AI]
Then, what is it?
It's Shangri-la.
What the hell is that?
How can something
like that fly anyway?
That thing has got
to be from the future.
Well, Tobi? What is it?
It's a ship known
as a Destructron,
sent here from Shangri-la.
It's a weapon used to
overlap and assimilate
all dimension into itself.
Now is not the time
to mess around!
What the hell does
that thing do?!
Eventually, this reality will
disappear into Shangri-la.
It's gonna do what?
Don't say it.
Haruka's who it wants.
I've seen this machine before...
I know I have...
Are you okay, Atori?!
[MIHO] Uh, that can't be real!
That has to be a mirage, right?!
Have you ever seen a mirage
that has that much detail, Miho?
It's fake, fake!
I don't want it to be real!
That thing's impossible!
You think that came
from the future too?!
The future?
Why is something like that
coming from the future?!
That's bad!
Pull yourself
together, will ya?!
[KUINA]
Dragon... Torque!
Who or what is this guy?!
[ISAMI]
Impossible!
[KUINA]
As long as I have you...!
Run, Haruka!
Let go of me!
Stop it, let her go!
[KUINA]
What's this?!
Yu, no!
[KUINA]
Noein... can you hear me?!
I've secured
the Dragon Torque!
Take me... Take me
with you to Shangri-la!
Noein!
Haruka...!
[KUINA]
Noein!
Now, release Haruka!
Look, it's him!
Karasu!
[KUINA]
How did you...?! You were...!
[KUINA groans]
[KUINA yells]
[KUINA]
I'm going to Shangri-la!
[NOEIN]
Don't meddle.
[KUINA]
Huh?
[NOEIN] I told you,
I no longer have a need
for your pathetic assistance.
[KUINA]
But I successfully captured
the Dragon Torque for you!
[NOEIN] You are unneccesary
in this dimension. Get lost.
[NOEIN]
Miserable fool.
Huh.
[KARASU] So, you
manipulated Kuina, Noein.
And you murdered Fukuro!
Noein!
[NOEIN]
How unfortunate.
I wanted to bring you
so much more suffering.
You can also collapse and die.
Look at him.
[HARUKA] Know that
you'll never be forgiven.
I could never forgive you
for the things you have done.
Haruka...!
[NOEIN]
That's...
[NOEIN] Why, the time
is quite right, indeed.
Haruka!
Are you alright?!
I'm okay. Thank you.
[MIHO]
What?
[AI]
They're gone.
Hey, that ship's gone too!
Who cares about that?
Haruka is missing!
[YU]
There she is!
Hey everyone! I'm okay.
It was Karasu who saved me.
He did, huh?
But he said he never could
have done it without you.
That because you
were fighting for me,
he had extra strength
to come to my rescue.
I did that?
[ISAMI]
There's nothing on it!
Not this one or that one!
Nothing's on here! I got
a real good picture of 'em,
but it's not here!
What do you mean it's not
on there? What'd ya do to it?!
I have no idea!
Is it possible this whole
thing was a hallucination?
No way.
We all know we saw him.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[HARUKA]
Of course I remember.
[KUINA] I will perform
a fix-reverse calculation.
[KOORIYAMA]
Even if we're killed,
we can ignore it if we have to.
[HARUKA]
Next Episode: Reminiscence.
Can you keep a happy
memory with you forever?