[BARON panting]
[HARUKA]
Grandma...
[BARON whines]
[HARUKA] You were in
the video too, huh, Baron?
This was 4 years ago, you know.
[HARUKA] Grandma was
doing fine back then.
I guess I shouldn't
expect anything
[BARON whines]
I promise, Haruka,
I'll write you all the time.
I'm sure she forgot about that.
[BARON barks]
Huh?
[KOORIYAMA]
Hey.
[UCHIDA]
Good mornin', Haruka.
Oh, hi Miss Uchida and
Mr. Kooriyama. How are you?
[KOORIYAMA] So, were you
expecting a letter or something?
Oh, no, not really.
I just remembered something
from the good ol' days.
That's kinda funny, you know?
Your good ol' days
are my recent ones.
[HARUKA]
Huh?
This'll make more sense
down the road,
but once you get older,
you forget more stuff
than you remember.
Do you forget stuff,
Mr. Kooriyama?
[KOORIYAMA]
Hm?
Have you ever
forgotten about somebody
who was important to you?!
Well, I don't know
if I've done that.
[KOORIYAMA]
I've had a long life so far
and I've met lots of people,
so I'm sure I've forgotten
someone along the way.
[HARUKA]
I won't forget.
[KOORIYAMA]
Hm?
I know I won't forget you.
No matter how old I am.
Well, thank you
very much, little lady.
[phone rings]
Hey, Ai, what's goin' on?
That's great! Is everyone
going to be there?
Yeah? Yeah. Oh, really?
[KOORIYAMA]
See you later.
Ah, hang on a sec.
Um... Did you guys
come here for a reason?
Nah, we just wanted to come
by and see how you were doin'.
Isn't that right, Uchida?
Right. I did have one question.
Has anythin' unusual
happened lately?
Depends on what you
mean by unusual.
It's all so weird, I've actually
kinda gotten used to it.
That's really incredible,
because I keep thinkin'
I'm gonna have a heart
attack any second now.
[HARUKA giggles]
Haruka, if you're
ever in danger,
or need our help, please
don't hesitate to call us.
Would you do that?
Thanks so much, you two.
[KOORIYAMA]
Take care.
[HARUKA]
Oh, hello? Sorry.
Okay, I got it.
Around 10 o'clock?
[KOORIYAMA]
She seems to be doin' okay.
[UCHIDA] Despite all the bizarre
things that are happenin'.
Kids are pretty resilient.
They seem to be able to
adapt better than adults
most of the time.
There somethin' on
your mind, Uchida?
That thing yesterday...
Officially it's bein' called
a weather phenomenon.
[KOORIYAMA] Big surprise,
they're calling it a mirage.
[UCHIDA] And that doesn't
upset you at all?
[KOORIYAMA]
Sounds like something
an arrogant adult
would think of.
[UCHIDA]
Yes, but...
Yeah, well,
even if we're killed,
we can just ignore
it if we have to.
[UCHIDA]
What did you say?
[KOORIYAMA] Oh, it's nothing.
I just remembered something
after talking to the girl.
So, what do you wanna do now?
I'll go and speak directly
with Professor Sasaki.
And ask him to stop the
Magic Circle Project?
You know what, Uchida?
I've been thinking...
Remember when we were
kids and we relied
on our senses and instincts?
Well, then we grew up and we
learned how society functions,
and we started to make
decisions using our smarts.
I don't know which is better...
[ISAMI] That thing yesterday
was definitely impossible,
but I'm totally positive
that it was real.
Of course it was real. We all
saw it with our own eyes.
[ISAMI] Yeah, but it doesn't
show up in any of the pictures.
It was quite obviously
a gigantic ghost!
Yeah, yeah...
D'you think everyone
forgot about it?
How could they?
I don't know, but it's like
no one talks about it anymore.
It's like anyone
who's older than us
just hates talking about
something weird going on.
Yeah, but I know that's
something we definitely saw.
So the next time it shows up,
I'll take it with this.
And then they'll know...
[ISAMI]
Dude...
Hey, who wants to go
get some ice cream?
I'm in! Hey, c'mon, let's go!
Wow, lately, he's really
been in a good mood.
I think we all know why.
You brought that for a reason?
I'll record it
next time for sure.
How can a video camera
make a guy that glad?
This from someone who gets
excited over a soccer ball?
This flower is really pretty.
[ATORI grunts]
What was that for?!
The flower didn't deserve that!
I was aiming for your head,
so why did I hit the flower?!
I just don't know...
Sure ya don't!
Talk! I know you're
up to something!
I don't know what you
could be talking about...
Don't play dumb! Talk!
[ATORI]
Stop! Please...
[TOBI]
Stop it, Kosagi!
Let go! He was able
to avoid my attack!
He regained his abilities!
Then why isn't he
dodging you now?!
If Atori was sane, he would've
fought back already!
[ATORI groaning]
[TOBI]
You okay, Atori?
[ATORI]
It hurts! It hurts...
[ATORI cackles]
[UCHIDA]
Do you really intend to approve
the Magic Circle Project?
This is wrong, Professor Sasaki!
[SASAKI] Uchida,
you haven't changed a bit
since you were a student.
You always jumped
to conclusions.
Science is never
about conclusions.
[UCHIDA]
I know it's about the process!
You drilled that into me
all through university!
You also told me that science
is the asset of all mankind.
That it wasn't to be
used for profiteerin'!
[SASAKI] True, Uchida.
But from the moment we realized
that science can be lucrative,
economics starts to make
its influence felt.
[UCHIDA]
But, Professor...!
[SASAKI] I'll talk with
Shinohara one more time.
Well, thank you.
Don't get the
wrong idea, Uchida.
This doesn't necessarily mean
that I believe your description.
The critical outbreak of the
overlapping of dimensions
as described in your report
is difficult to assimilate.
I merely want to watch over
the extent of your research
a little longer.
[UCHIDA]
I understand, Professor.
[SHINOHARA] Shut down the
Magic Circle Project? Sasaki!
I think you're insane!
We've detected an abnormality
in the quantum potential.
As a member of the Absolute
Critical Prevention
Planning Committee, I cannot
approve Magic Circle Project's
marine experiment
under those conditions.
[SHINOHARA]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SASAKI]
There are safety issues!
I don't think you understand
the big picture, Professor.
Y'see, Ab-Com is
merely an adornment.
The Government's excuse
so that they can claim
that they're thinkin'
of the people's safety
and the environment.
Perhaps you should consider
who you should thank
for being able to spend time
in such an...
extravagant laboratory.
Yes, but--
We're using this project
to pry open the door
of quantum mechanics!
It will result in
a new revolution
of computer networking!
It won't just be communications,
the entire world
will be changed.
It's time for a transformation.
We will create a new world!
Who the hell are you to
tell me to call it off, huh?!
I didn't say you
should call it off.
All I'm asking you to do
is momentarily
reconsider the project.
Hah. Sounds just a
little weak to me.
If we stop this now,
you won't get any further
funding for your labs.
So I'm gonna forget you
told me to reconsider
and let's go full-force on this.
The Mayuzumi approach to quantum
mechanics will be proven.
I refuse to go along.
There is no way I can
approve an experiment
that is as dangerous as this is!
[AI]
Going to the pool might be fun.
[MIHO]
But it'd be lame if we have
to wear our school swimsuits.
[ISAMI] I get sick
from swallowing the water.
Yeah, 'cause you're
a lousy swimmer.
[ISAMI] Yeah, so what?
There's no need to force myself
to go in the water.
I can live just
fine on dry land.
[AI]
Excuses, excuses...
[MIHO]
How pathetic.
[ISAMI]
What'd you just say?!
[AI]
Chill out, Isami.
Hey, is something wrong, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
Huh? Is that Aya...?
Huh!
[YU] What are you doing?!
Where are you going?!
[HARUKA] Aya, is that you?
You are Aya, right?
[AYA'S MOM]
Oh my, it's little Haruka!
It's been such a
long time, how are you?
Fine, thanks. It's nice to see
you! Are you here on vacation?
[AYA'S MOM] Yes, sightseeing
over summer break!
That sounds like fun!
Just like old times!
You were inseparable!
Aya, do you remember
how lonely you were
when Haruka moved
out of the city?
Uhh... yeah...
Haruka, will you please
start writing to Aya again?
[HARUKA]
Sure!
Um, Mom? I don't remember her...
[HARUKA gasps]
[AYA]
Are you really moving away?
[HARUKA]
Yeah..
[AYA] I'm gonna write you
letters all the time, okay?
[HARUKA]
Really?!
Of course, I swear it!
Is that someone you knew
back when you lived in Tokyo?
[HARUKA]
Yeah, it's Aya.
She's totally
forgotten about me!
Hey, Haruka, don't let it get to
ya! You've got us now, right?!
[HARUKA]
It's not like that...
It doesn't really
bother me that much.
I was just a little
surprised, that's all.
Who cares about her anyway?!
Our friendship is eternal!
It will never end!
Yeah, well, you'd be
the first one to forget.
That's so rude, Isami!
How dare you?!
[HARUKA]
Oh, I forgot! I gotta go!
My mom asked me
to pick up a few things.
[AI]
What?
[HARUKA]
I'm sorry, see you later!
[AI]
Haruka!
This isn't good...
What do you mean?
She took off!
You heard her, she has
to get stuff for her mom.
You're such a moron.
Can't you see she's totally
lying about that?!
[ISAMI]
What?! Really?
[AI] Obviously, she's pretty
bummed out about Aya.
I should go see if she's okay.
Good idea. Knowing her,
she'd get even more depressed
if we all went to cheer her up.
[KUINA] I will perform a
fixed-reverse calculation!
[ALL gasp]
What did you just say?!
Was that a...
reverse calculation?!
[KUINA]
Correct. We have Dragon Torque's
quantum composition
data on file.
If I recompose the Reizu
according to its data,
I can bring the
Dragon Torque to La'cryma.
[TAIZA]
Out of the question!
To perform a fixed-reverse
calculation would require
the full processing power
of La'cryma's Reizu simulator!
The lines would be
temporarily lost!
What if Shangri-la were to
attack at that moment, huh?!
We would be defenseless!
[KUINA] Then is there
a better solution?!
[KUINA] Commencing now.
Is that acceptable?
[AI]
Hello, anyone home?
What? Oh.
Haruka's out right now.
Would it be okay if
we waited for her?
Yes, of course. Why don't you
wait in her room upstairs.
[ISAMI]
Yes ma'am.
Oh, there's snacks and juice in
the kitchen, so help yourselves.
[phone rings]
[KOORIYAMA]
This is Kooriyama.
[KOORIYAMA] I've just been
pulled off this assignment.
They just ordered
me to get back.
Looks like I'm not
gonna be able to be
your bodyguard anymore.
[UCHIDA]
What d'you mean?!
Well, Chairman Sazaki of
Ab-Com has just resigned.
And his replacement,
some geezer named Toby,
is gonna remove
you from Ab-Com.
Oh no...
I'm afraid it's just
the usual dirty method.
[AIDA] I think Marukai's
just moved to platform three.
Hold on...
This is 6 to 3, do you copy?
You got 'im yet.
3 to 6, I just got him
in my sight. Hm.
[KOORIYAMA]
6 to 3, roger. Don't rush it.
[TEENAGER]
Hey, Mr. Detective.
Heh, I just wanted to know.
Did you enjoy the almond jelly?
What the hell'd you do?!
[TEENAGER cackling]
[MAN]
Somebody fell on the tracks!
Aida!
[KOORIYAMA]
Aida, where are you?!
Huh?
Aida, hang on!
[KOORIYAMA] They covered up
the murder of my colleague
by calling it an
impulsive suicide.
[UCHIDA] Didn't the police
investigate it properly?
[KOORIYAMA]
The case was a spy incident
going up as high as
a resident ambassador.
We couldn't make it
public knowledge.
That's really awful...
Wait, where are you goin' now?
[KOORIYAMA] Even if we
leak this to the media,
Shinohara will just
cover it up. He always does.
Yeah, I'm sure he will.
[KOORIYAMA] Well, I'm not
gonna give up this time.
Even if it kills me.
Let's go, Uchida.
I think the only thing
we can do right now
is to find Dr. Mayuzumi. Coming?
Uh-huh.
[HARUKA]
I was starting to forget...
...about my grandmother...
I don't understand,
because I loved her so much.
I'll gradually forget
her smile... her voice...
...each and every
day that passes.
[HARUKA]
Wow, that's cute!
Thanks, Grandma!
[YU] Your grandmother
died two years ago, right?
It's hard to keep remembering
people who have passed away.
It's something you can't help.
[HARUKA] Eventually,
everyone forgets each other.
Just the way Aya
forgot all about me...
And how I forgot
about Grandma...
But there are some things
you'll never forget!
Yeah?
Of course. I mean,
I still remember
how you and I first met
like it was yesterday.
It was summer break
in 2nd grade.
You came to my house
with Baron and your mom.
[YU]
You totally forgot.
How could you not remember that?
I mean, it wasn't
even that long ago.
[HARUKA]
I didn't forget.
I totally remember.
I remember because
I was so nervous.
We had just moved here.
And I was so happy when
you were nice to me.
[YU] Hey, let's head back.
I told everybody
to head over to your house
and that we'd meet up
with them there later.
[HARUKA]
Okay.
I might be wrong,
but I think you used to
hold my hand back then.
Wow, you remember
the weirdest details.
[OPERATOR] Undulation function
approaching three values.
[OPERATOR]
Commence data transport.
[KUINA] Commence dimension
transport countdown.
[KUINA]
I'm ready... Dragon Torque.
[HARUKA]
Oh, you're all here.
This stuff's really amazing.
Check it out!
You're right, it is,
just don't get in the way.
I'm not a child.
Hey, Tobi, what's this
thing over here do?
[TOBI]
Wait, Isami. Don't touch it.
Knock it off.
Atori, would you like to
visit the mountain sometime?
I think I would.
That sounds like fun.
Where's Karasu?
He went to go check out an area
with a high rate of
dimensional change.
[ATORI gasps]
Atori, what's wrong?
What is it?
[ATORI]
This is bad! Very bad! Listen!
The wind has started
howling again!
Tobi.
I need an explanation.
Tell me quickly!
[OPERATOR] Fixed-reverse
calculation rate 72%.
Stop this!
[AI]
Is that blue snow?!
Impossible!
Reversed calculation?!
What the heck is that?
It has to be Kuina!
He must be trying to transport
Haruka back to La'cryma!
This dimension is wavering!
[KOSAGI]
Karasu, this undulation!
I've never felt this
kind of pressure!
Is it... La'cryma?
Haruka...!
Karasu?!
Look at that!
[ASUKA humming]
Haruka!
Stay back! You'll get pulled
in if you get too close!
Yu!
Haruka!
Karasu!
[HARUKA]
Oh no!
[KARASU]
Haruka!
[ATORI laughing]
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
It's supposed to be
15 years into the future.
[KOSAGI]
But it's not necessary for me.
[KUINA]
Then come with me to Shangri-la!
[HARUKA]
Next Episode: "Once More."
Will I see you again?