You died and left me
all alone, didn't you?
[NOEIN] That's right...
My Haruka is dead.
She died right in front of me
in the summer when we were 17.
[AI]
Haruka!
[ISAMI]
Where are you guys? Yu?
[MIHO]
Hey, come on out!
Yeah! Where are you?!
Hey, Ai!
No! You must leave here!
I think I heard her,
it was her voice!
Where are you?! Come on, now!
We've come for you,
let's go home! Haruka!
I'm sorry, I can't...
[ISAMI]
What is that thing?
[AI]
That's not a rainbow...
[ATORI] The Uroboros. It's bad.
We are in grave danger.
What's wrong, Atori?
You should go inside the house.
[MIHO]
Oh.
What's the deal
with that?! We can--
[ATORI]
Be quiet! I said go inside!
This dimension is an
illusion to all of you!
It simply doesn't exist.
There's only one thing real
to you in this dimension,
and it's that
damned house there!
Fine! What about our friends?!
Yeah! We are not gonna
leave 'em behind!
Stop fighting me on this!
You kids are still too
young to understand.
[MIHO]
Atori...
We can't just leave
our friends behind
and only try to save ourselves.
[JILL]
Run, Atori...
Run for it... They'll get you...
[ATORI]
No, I can't just leave you.
You have to go...
[ATORI] We all swore we'd run
away down south together.
If we all make it, we won't have
to freeze to death anymore.
And then the adults will
never hurt us again.
We can all live by ourselves.
Remember that, Jill.
[ATORI yells]
[ATORI screams]
[ATORI]
Come on now, guys.
You're just going to have
to trust me on this one, yes?
I swear I will
find your friends.
Send them back. Send them back!
[ISAMI] Oh, man, that
was weird. Are you alright?
What the heck just happened?
Felt like an earthquake.
[MIHO]
Atori, what was that?
Haruka.
Amazing. Simply amazing.
You truly are the best.
I'll never trust you!
You lied to me!
[NOEIN]
You and I will become one.
To resolve my sorrows,
I need you.
Check out all that
stuff up there.
That's impossible!
[ATORI]
This is really bad...
I think the dimensions
are converging.
This can't be!
[KARASU] The dimensional
convergence has begun.
[YU]
The dimensional convergence?
Noein has begun to use Haruka's
power to complete his goal.
What are her powers?
We need to get to her soon.
Haruka...
[YU]
Karasu, over there!
What's going on? Karasu?
It's starting now.
Don't be afraid of them.
Think only of Haruka.
You understand? Concentrate,
and the path will lead to her.
Turn me loose! I gotta go, now!
[ISAMI]
Damn!
[AI]
No, don't!
Haruka is trying to send
you all back to your world.
She's what?
Hey, we can just
leave 'em! We gotta help!
I swear to you that I will bring
them back safely, alright?
Then I'm staying right here!
Come on. Can't you
trust me, just a little?
[MIHO]
Atori?
I... hope you find your sister.
She died a long while ago...
What?!
She stepped on a land
mine and got blown up.
That wasn't right.
Don't you children
make the same mistake.
Take care.
[MIHO]
Ah, wait!
Where are you going?
Sorry, but I can't
predict the future.
But you know, it's interesting
because we don't know
what happens next.
You kids play nice.
Well, now. I guess
I'll have to go find
that sorry-looking loser.
[NOEIN]
You sent them home?
But I was going to integrate
them into this dimension.
You have always brought
me nothing but grief.
I did?
The you in every
single dimension
brings the me in every
dimension nothing but sorrow.
They're coming!
[YU]
They're going to land, Karasu!
They're encircling us.
What's going on?
What the heck are those things?
And how come they
keep getting bigger?
They're reacting to
our emotional status.
Huh? They're reacting to us?
Noein wills this.
He's ticked off because we're
trying to save Haruka, right?
I will take care of these
things. You go after Haruka!
Myself?
You will do it. Go.
[OPERATOR 1] Position fixed
on vessels 1 through 6.
[OPERATOR 2]
Start countdown from 20.
[OPERATOR 3]
Firing device, ready.
[OPERATOR 1]
Acceleration coil, ready.
Start countdown on my mark.
Deploy radiator panels.
Do it already!
[OPERATOR 3]
All vessels.
[SHINOHARA cackles]
[SHINOHARA]
And now, we have taken
the first step towards history!
Can you understand
my sheer excitement?!
[SHINOHARA cackles]
[SHINOHARA]
Let's dance, Mayuzumi!
[KOSAGI groans]
What's wrong?!
Don't worry about us!
Go on, get going!
I'm so sorry, but we're
unable to go on...
Why, Tobi?!
Our existence is
beginning to be erased
by the wavering of the
quanta in the Magic Circle.
[KOORIYAMA, UCHIDA gasp]
[TOBI] I'm afraid you'll
have to go on without us.
[KOORIYAMA]
Come on, let's go.
We have to trust
they'll get it done.
[YU]
Now what?
[THE OTHERS]
We committed a grave error.
[YU] What do you mean?
I'm looking for Haruka.
I don't suppose you have
any way of knowing
how I could get her back...
[THE OTHERS]
Can you stop Noein?
I don't know that for sure...
But I will save her!
[THE OTHERS] If so, I will
deliver you to the accelerator.
[ASUKA] See?! It's gone,
Miyuki! It's really gone!
And Haruka's gone too!
She was in it!
[MIYUKI]
Asu, you have to calm down!
Huh?
[MIYUKI]
Blue snow...?
[ASUKA]
What?
The house!
It's back!
[MIYUKI]
It came back...
Atori?!
Wait a minute!
What the... Impossible!
We're back? Really?
[ASUKA] Kids, what happened?!
Where did all of you go?!
Where's Yu? Are Haruka and
my son with you guys?!
Uhh...
I'm not sure you're
gonna believe us
if we say where she is...
Is it true?! I heard your
house disappeared!
Uh... What's going on?
[OPERATOR 1]
Quantum acceleration 65%.
Critical mass will be
achieved in 13 minutes.
[SHINOHARA cackles]
Spin! Yeah, spin for me, baby!
[NOEIN] You know this
dimension was formed
by the accumulation
of all sorrows.
That is why people had
obliterated their existences.
The existence of
mankind leads to sorrow.
Recognition can also be the
beginning of misunderstanding.
That is why people stopped
recognizing each other,
obliterated their
individual existences,
and become a
collective consciousness.
Yu!
Haruka!
Let her go, right now!
[NOEIN]
Oh, so you invited him as well.
Alright then, I will show you.
Come now, Haruka.
Dragon Torque...
There is no need
to choose a future.
All possible dimensions will
now become one with Shangri-la.
[YU]
Run, Haruka!
[UCHIDA]
Shut this down, now!
The surrounding quanta
will begin to resonate,
that means destruction!
[SHINOHARA]
I have no interest whatsoever
in the opinion of an amateur.
[UCHIDA]
You think this is a joke?!
[KOORIYAMA]
Nobody move!
Now stop this thing!
[UCHIDA] Dr. Mayuzumi,
shut down this system!
Cute little gun...
[KOORIYAMA]
Shut up!
If you're gonna carry,
then carry this!
But you probably couldn't afford
it on your crappy salary.
How about I arrest you
for threatening an officer?
Shut the hell up!
Listen, do ya hear that?
That's the sound of
a new era starting.
8 minutes and 30 seconds
until critical mass.
What the hell is that thing...?
[KOSAGI] Did you see that?
What's happening?
[TOBI]
It's the Uroboros!
[ENRA]
It's fading!
I'm fading away...
Ahh, Enra!
The final barrier
limes are collapsing!
No! It can't be!
Oops! I think I shot him!
Oh well, self defense.
Kooriyama, no!
Ahh! Leave him be!
Bastard...
I warned you, didn't I?!
Shinohara! I started this
experiment to benefit mankind,
not to destroy it!
[SHINOHARA]
So what?!
[UCHIDA]
Dr. Mayuzumi!
[SHINOHARA] Did you think I
was oblivious to your plan?!
Did you really think
I wouldn't notice
you took down our security
to sneak these guys inside?!
So shut up and watch!
[YU]
Look out!
Don't interfere,
you little fool.
[NOEIN] You're actually
still going to fight me?
[YU]
I won't let you beat me!
[NOEIN]
I have no need of you.
Only one of us is necessary.
No!
[HARUKA]
Yu!
I so love to hate you.
Stop it, now!
[YU]
Karasu?!
That's right.
We are the same person.
Oh, if only I could
do it all over again...
I would go back to when
I was a boy like you...
[YU]
Don't mock me!
Your eyes are still
innocent and untainted.
It breaks my heart,
knowing those eyes
will become so deeply etched...
...with painful sorrow.
What're you talkin' about?!
[NOEIN]
Eventually, you are going to
experience great sadness.
A sadness so profound, you will
believe your life is cursed.
[HARUKA]
You're lying!
[YU]
Haruka!
I refuse to
believe those things!
Alright. I suppose I'll
just have to show you.
[YUKIE]
You've all grown up so much.
[ISAMI]
Of course we have. We're 17 now.
Has it really been 5 years
since you graduated?
Ms. Yukie, in 5 years you
haven't changed one bit.
Ha! Thanks a lot!
I see you've also learned
the art of kissing up.
[ISAMI]
Dude!
We're packed in
kinda tight back here.
Well, I guess you shoulda put
a little more
thought into it then.
Who me?
Yeah, you. He hasn't
been back from Tokyo
in a really long time.
You coulda let him
sit next to Haruka,
then you'd have the front seat.
Hey, knock it off, guys.
Great, now I feel
like a real jerk.
Hey, Ms. Yukie, step on it.
We'll be there in no time,
the way you drive.
Hey, you know what?
We're going fast enough.
[AI] It's too bad
Miho couldn't make it.
[ISAMI]
She had a wedding to attend.
[YU] By the way, what are
getting at the store--?
[HARUKA]
Yu...
Please...
Help me...
Haruka--!
[NOEIN] In an instant,
I lost all of my friends...
...and the woman I loved.
Can you understand the sorrow?
The sorrow of the one
who is left behind?
[NOEIN] I experienced a
moment where the world
ceases to have any meaning.
Haruka...
Why did you desert me...
...and leave me all alone?!
You left!
[NOEIN sobbing]
[NOEIN]
Why did you do it?
[NOEIN] Why must I
take all the suffering?
I kept wandering
and kept searching...
...through every
dimension for you.
Hoping to find my Haruka...
But then...
...I finally understood.
I have come to realize
that in every dimension,
there is nothing
but pain and sorrow.
[NOEIN]
Everywhere there was death.
Everywhere there was pain...
...steeped in sorrow.
[HARUKA]
Yu, help me!
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Yu, help me!
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Yu, help meee!
[YU]
Harukaaa!
[NOEIN] Mankind does not simply
just exist in this dimension...
When people recognize
the dimension they see,
that dimension gains existence.
So, in reality,
the ultimate observer
is each and every
living human being.
That is why I lost hope.
All the dimensions cannot escape
the chain of unhappiness.
It started out all wrong.
[NOEIN] That is why I will
integrate every reality
into Shangri-la...
...and return it
all to nothingness.
[NOEIN] If we return all
to nothingness, the dimension
will be reborn
from the beginning,
and branch off, giving birth
to a new universe.
I know that a better dimension
will be born this time.
[NOEIN]
Come. Come to me.
[NOEIN] To release these people
from every kind of suffering.
From nothingness, let's bring
a new dimension into existence.
I hold the future in my hands!
[SHINOHARA cackles]
[OPERATOR 2]
10 seconds to critical mass!
It's happening!
Come to me, Haruka.
Come now.
Haruka!
[NOEIN] Because you
no longer have a future.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[NOEIN] Dragon Torque, come with
me to a world of nothingness.
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "The Beginning."
Please grant everyone's wishes.