[FUKURO]
Don't let it hit the ground!
[KOSAGI]
Where's Karasu?
[FUKURO]
Go around to the left!
[KOSAGI]
Not again. It has a shield.
[FUKURO grunts]
[KOSAGI grunting]
[KARASU grunts]
[FUKURO]
Karasu has gotten through!
[KARASU grunting, yelling]
[FUKURO]
It's no good. It's collapsing.
Get away from there, Karasu!
Karasu, no!
[HARUKA sighs]
[HARUKA] Hey, will you stop.
This is for mom.
Baron, you've gotten
awfully fat lately.
[HARUKA] Mom! Wake up,
breakfast is ready.
[ASUKA]
Haruka, what time is it?
It's already past eight.
I've gotta get to school, okay?
I'm leaving. Bye!
[ASUKA] See ya later, Honey.
Have a nice day!
That was definitely a ghost.
[MIHO]
They wander around aimlessly
without even realizing
that they're dead.
[MIHO] Whatever you do,
[HARUKA] Morning.
[MIHO]
don't ever speak to a ghost...
...'cause if you do, you'll get
pulled into the spirit world.
--Good morning, Ai.
--[AI] Hi, Haruka. Good morning.
What's going on
over there anyway?
[AI] Miho's telling all
about the supernatural.
Oh, I see.
[AI] Kyoko from class 2
says she saw a ghost
in the alley behind the church.
[HARUKA] A ghost?
[school bell rings]
Yeah, a ghost
wearing a black coat.
[YUKIE] Alright everyone.
The bell has rung, class.
Take your seats right away.
Let's have a discussion
about the summer break
after homeroom, alright?
[ISAMI]
Miss Yukie?
[YUKIE]
Yes, Isami?
Will you go on a date with me
during summer break?
[YUKIE laughs] I'm so sorry,
but my date card
is all booked up for
the next three years.
[STUDENTS giggling]
No way!
[BOY]
Loser.
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Be sure to watch out for cars
on the way home from school.
[GIRL] I'll see you later!
[YUKIE] No running in the halls!
[AI] Oh yeah, tomorrow night,
you wanna get together
and test your courage
for a night of fright?
Why not?
We'll hunt for ghosts.
It's summer break,
we can stay out late,
so let's all go together.
[AI] What do you say, Isami?
Do you want to go out
for a night of fright?
Did you say night of fright?
Yeah, we're gonna go out tonight
and hunt for ghosts.
Man, you guys are ridiculous.
You mean to say you
still believe in ghosts?
There's no way stuff
like ghosts exists.
It's scientifically impossible.
What a bunch of losers.
Right, Yu?
I don't think so. There are
still things that happen
in this world that can't
be explained by science.
Wrong-o. Listen, there are
no such things as ghosts.
Oh yeah, then let's go
together to make sure?
Well, I guess that settles it.
You're gonna come
with us, Isami.
What? I don't wanna.
Why do I gotta go anyway?
What's the matter?
Don't tell me you're scared.
No, I'm not afraid of any
ghosts. Isn't that right, Yu?
I have to go to cram school,
so I can't go.
But I thought...
[HARUKA]
Yu, wait up!
Where you going?
Are you mad about something?
No. I've just got
a lot on my mind.
Wha...?
[ISAMI]
Man, Yu's been actin'
kind of bizarre
lately, you know?
[AI]
He can't help it.
Yu has middle school
exams coming up soon.
[HARUKA]
Yu!
[YU]
How long do I have to stay here?
Will I ever be able
to get... out?
[KOORIYAMA]
Hey, did you know?
Did I know what?
That this is the first
day of summer break.
Oh, it's summer break?
I haven't had any kind of
break for five years.
[computer whirring]
It's appeared again.
Maybe just pickin' up some
kinda radio signal, huh?
Don't pretend to
know everything.
Relax. How you gonna
report it to headquarters?
They won't give me
the time of day
with this pitiful
amount of data.
Well, then you're
just gonna have to
try a whole lot harder, Uchida.
You are the last person
that should be tellin' me that.
And please don't smoke
those filthy things in here.
[HARUKA] Oh wow, look at
the time! Gotta go, bye!
[AI] See you later.
Have a good one, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
I will!
[KOORIYAMA]
Summer break, huh?
[UCHIDA]
Huh?
[MIYUKI]
Yu?
[YU]
Yeah, Mom?
[MIYUKI] Do you understand that
summer school starts today?
[YU]
Yeah.
[MIYUKI] For summer break
I want you to concentrate
only on your studies.
[YU]
I know, Mom.
[MIYUKI]
Yu...
...you can do this.
You must have discipline.
[MIYUKI]
Yu...
I think it's best if you
stop seeing your friends.
At least for the time being.
Don't you think?
[ASUKA]
Night of fright?
[HARUKA] Yeah, we're doing
it tomorrow night.
It's okay, isn't it?
Just 'cause it's summer break
doesn't mean you can goof off
for the next three months.
But I'm not goofing off! I made
this lunch for us, didn't I?
[ASUKA]
This is slightly uncooked.
It's al dente.
It's supposed to be like that.
If you have a problem,
you make lunch.
But Haruka, you made me
a promise to do all the cooking,
at least until I finish
my manuscript, remember?
I remember. Just stop
your complaining.
You don't know how hard
it is for a single mother
to raise a kid all on her own.
Dad's paying you alimony
and child support, isn't he?
Look here, you...
It's no secret, Mother...
you forget I'm gonna be
in middle school
next year, you know?
Listen Miss Know-it-all,
are you saying
--that mothers shouldn't work?
--No, that's not what I meant
[ASUKA] That they should stay
at home cooking and cleaning?
[HARUKA] I just don't get
why you spend all your time
making comic books
that don't sell.
[ASUKA]
Please, don't say that.
[HARUKA]
Oh no, I must have dozed off.
[CHILDREN laughing, shouting]
[HARUKA] Yu! Have you been
studying all this time?
You're dedicated.
What are you doin' here anyway?
[YU] Why were you waiting
in front of the cram school?
[HARUKA]
I was killing time.
[YU]
You could get into trouble
walking around
this time of night.
[HARUKA] If you're gonna worry
about something like that,
then you shouldn't be
running away from home.
Well you're the one who
said that we should
run away in the first place...
Just because you wanted to go
to your dad's house in Tokyo.
[HARUKA]
Yu? Wanna run away from home?
Let's go to Tokyo together.
I was having a fight with
my mom when I said that.
My parents are divorced,
and it's kinda complicated.
And I was really
missing my father.
You're a liar. I was an
idiot to listen to you.
[HARUKA]
Yu!
Would you wait just a second?
[YU]
Just forget it. Go home.
[HARUKA] I'm not a liar.
You need to have a plan
before running away from home.
[YU]
I know that.
Even if I did run away,
they'd just find me.
And then I'd be taken home.
So what's the point?
Sometimes... I wish
I could just run away.
I'll never get outta this town.
I'm gonna be here forever.
But that's not true.
Once you're an adult,
you'll be able to go
anywhere you want to.
I really wanna leave here.
Why aren't I an adult?
Yu...
[YU] I hate being a kid.
I just wish I could
get outta this stupid town.
[YU sobbing]
[HARUKA]
Yu...
I think... I think
I'm going crazy.
Yu...
[HARUKA gasps]
That's strange... blue snow?
Huh?
It's him.
[HARUKA yelps]
[KARASU]
The Dragon Torque.
[KARASU gasping]
[HARUKA]
He vanished.
[AI]
Hey, did ya hear?
[HARUKA]
Hear what?
[AI] I got an email from Saeko.
She said that the other night
a headless ghost
appeared at the mall.
[HARUKA]
Did you say ghost?
[AI] Yeah. And she said he
was wearing a black cape.
[HARUKA]
A black cape?
Yeah, you know what,
I've seen him too.
And he was wearing a black cape.
What? Wait, are you saying you
saw a ghost too? Where was he?
[HARUKA] I don't know.
Does it matter? Who cares?
I do. Now tell me where he was.
[KOORIYAMA]
Uh, excuse me, young ladies.
Listen, do you girls live
around here abouts?
Maybe you young ladies
could do me a big favor.
There's somethin'
I'm checking into.
I'll make it worth your while
if you girls help me out.
[KOORIYAMA]
I'll get you some juice.
It'll have to be canned though.
Ah! I totally forgot.
We gotta go, Haruka!
[HARUKA] What is it, Ai?
[KOORIYAMA] Hey!
Well that was strange.
I guess they don't
like canned juice.
[AI]
That guy was definitely a perv.
Did you see the way
he was looking at us?
We should really
call the police.
Hey, don't worry.
He acts suspicious,
but he's really not like that.
[AI]
Hm?
[phone ringing]
[KOORIYAMA] Hey, it's Kooriyama.
So, how you doin', Uchida?
How are things goin' over there?
[UCHIDA]
It looks like the data analysis
of the observation satellite
is complete in Tokyo.
[KOORIYAMA]
And?
And it's definite.
They confirmed an irregularity.
[KOORIYAMA sighs] Looks like
we're gonna be here a while.
Yeah, it looks that way.
[KOORIYAMA]
What do we do now?
[UCHIDA] I'm tryin' to
figure that out right now,
while I'm on this mountain top.
[YU sighs]
[banging]
[YU]
I'm going to cram school.
[MIYUKI]
Alright. Be careful.
[ISAMI]
Hey man.
I know that a night of fright
sounds kinda stupid,
but it may not be so bad.
[YU] Isami... you're afraid,
aren't you?
[ISAMI laughs nervously]
Don't be ridiculous.
Hey, look who's here.
Yeah, Yu came along!
I'm not sure if this is really
such a good idea, bro.
[MIHO] I'm sure we'll
see one tonight. I can tell.
I'm getting an eerie feeling.
Like right now, I can feel every
pore in my skin opening up.
[ISAMI] Uh, you know...
the path is dangerous,
so maybe we should go now.
What's the matter? Are you
scared or something, Isami?
Me? No way, I'm not afraid.
[MIHO] Come on you guys,
let's go this way.
I bet that Miho...
...probably doesn't even
believe in ghosts.
She's just doing this
to scare us. Hm?
[MIHO]
Hey everybody, whatcha doin'?
Come on over here. Let's get
this expedition started!
What's the matter?
I thought I saw a light.
Hey, knock it off.
[MIHO]
What's the matter?
[AI] I saw some kind of
light over there.
What? Oh no way.
I bet it's a flying ghost!
A flying ghost is
going through here!
It's a flying ghost?
That's impossible.
What's that?
Huh? A flying ghost!
[YU]
Huh?
[ISAMI]
Man, we're busted.
[MIHO]
Hey, what's going on?
[HARUKA]
Mrs. Goto...
You should be at the
cram school doing your studies.
[MIYUKI] I can't believe you'd
do something like this.
Hey, wait a minute. Mrs. Goto!
This is what happens when
you see these children.
[OPERATOR]
Coordinate fix complete.
Countdown.
[KARASU grunting]
[ISAMI] Well that kinda
took the fun out of it.
Come on now, don't be like that.
If you wanna have
any kind of encounter,
you have to wish hard
with all your might.
Wish hard? That's how you do it?
[MIHO] That's right. Alright
now, everybody wish! Yeah!
Mr. Ghost! Mr. Ghost,
please come out!
[ISAMI] I'm sure there has
to be another way to do this.
[AI]
Hey, are you worried about Yu?
Huh? No. I was just thinking.
Oh honestly.
Haruka, your feelings are
written all over your face.
W-What?
[MIYUKI] The cram school
called, and they said
you hadn't shown up yet.
I was so humiliated.
What were you doing out so late
at night with those other kids?
[MIYUKI] Haruka's mother
let her be there, didn't she?
She allows the girl
to run around wild.
Her mother is far too lenient.
[YU]
I...
Huh?
[YU]
I'm going... I'm going crazy.
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
Huh? Blue snow.
It's happening again.
[AI]
What's the matter, Haruka?
Just look at that.
It's snow. Blue snow.
Huh? Blue snow?
Oh quit it. There can't be snow
in the middle of summer.
Ai...
It's getting late.
Haven't you had enough?
[MIHO] No, I'm not going
home until I see one.
[ISAMI] But I'm starving.
I really think we should
head back soon, don't you?
Miho!
[ISAMI]
I can't see...
What's wrong with this?
The battery's dead.
Isami... look over there.
Uh, what? What's that?
It's a shadow.
It's a shadow from a tree.
What's going on, Miho?
[MIHO]
I see one.
Huh? See one what?
[KARASU groaning]
[KARASU screams]
[AI, MIHO scream]
[ISAMI whimpers]
[ISAMI yelps, whimpers]
It's touching my leg.
[KARASU groans]
[ISAMI whimpering]
What's the matter, Miho?
[HARUKA]
Miho!
Come on. Run, Haruka!
[HARUKA] Huh?
[AI] Hurry!
[OPERATOR]
One bird has disappeared.
Seven birds remain.
[KARASU] A reaction to the
high density Reizu...
Aren't ghosts supposed
to be legless?
It's impossible. That thing
couldn't have been real.
[MIHO]
That is definitely a ghost.
We have seen a ghost tonight!
Isn't that amazing?
Why are you so happy?
Listen, that was not a ghost.
[AI]
What?
It's too strange.
Well, he can't help
being strange. He is a ghost.
Huh?
It's coming this way.
[AI]
Huh?
What is it?
We have to get away.
Haruka, what's wrong?
Hey, hurry guys. Come on, hurry.
[MIHO] Something is flying,
and it's coming right at us!
[ISAMI]
Impossible.
[HARUKA]
Everybody run for it! Hurry!
[KARASU]
Is that it?
This can't be happening!
Apparently it's a
land-bound ghost.
I don't get it.
What's happening?
[HARUKA]
He's after me.
I've gotta get him
away from the others.
[ALL panting]
[HARUKA panting]
[HARUKA yelps]
[HARUKA]
Stay back!
[HARUKA gasps]
[ALL panting]
It's gone. It's not
chasing us now.
Are you sure about that?
[MIHO]
I wonder where it went.
[YU]
Where's Haruka?
[ISAMI]
Wait! I thought she was with us!
Wait a sec. You look familiar.
[HARUKA]
I know who you are.
You are...
[YU]
Haruka!
Huh?
[YU grunts]
Oh, Yu.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Answer me.
[KARASU] I get it now.
This dimension must be...
[KARASU cackling]
I'm afraid you can't do it.
You see, there is nothing
at all that you can do
to protect the young lady.
Who are you?
Can't you see? I'm you.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again.
That summer day's dream...
Oh crap, my right arm
didn't make it.
[HARUKA]
What's happening?
You are very lucky.
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "Runaway."
Who are you?