[OPERATOR] Fixed-reverse
calculation complete.
[KUINA]
She's here!
[KUINA laughs]
[KUINA] Dragon Torque! I have
waited a long time for you!
[HARUKA gasps]
[KUINA]
What?!
Karasu!
[HARUKA]
Yu!
Stop that!
[KUINA]
You dare appear with me again?!
[KARASU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
No!
Let go of him, right now!
[HARUKA]
Yu!
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Yu...!
Where are we?
We're in an underground city...
A what?
It's called "La'cryma."
[YU]
I don't understand.
It's fifteen years
in the future.
Fifteen years?!
[ATORI laughing]
Where'd they disappear to?
What? Atori, are you alright?
But... they're gone!
That's impossible!
It's La'cryma! They were
both teleported there!
[KARASU]
Why didn't you prevent it?!
I'm sorry!
Send me to La'cryma right now!
It can't be done, Karasu!
I don't have enough
equipment with me
to construct a
transportation system!
[ATORI]
Knock it off.
This is not the time
for an argument.
Atori...
You're yourself again.
Come on, Tobi, think.
What are you saying?
If any person can
do it, it's you.
I know you can bring back
those annoying brats.
[KOORIYAMA]
Looks like everything's okay.
[UCHIDA] Yes, but I felt
a powerful dimensional bend.
You saw that light, didn't you?
I guess I did.
[UCHIDA]
Somethin' has happened.
[KOORIYAMA]
Huh?
[TOBI] Oh. Hello, Ms. Uchida.
What perfect timing.
I was just about to go
out looking for you.
Oh?
[TORI] Let me ask; you own
a quantum computer, right?
[UCHIDA] That machine
is still only a prototype.
Will it be okay?
[TORI] It's better than
the Noiman model.
[YU]
What is this place?
Why are they living
underground like this?
[HARUKA] I don't think they
can live on the surface.
But how? Why? What exactly
happens to us in the future?
[HARUKA]
I'm not really sure.
But something really
terrible happened then.
From what I know,
they were being attacked
by these weird, flying things.
And, in order to survive,
they decided to leave the
surface and move underground.
Who told that to you? That
doesn't make any sense at all.
[YU]
Then again...
Who would've imagined that
this would be our future?
I've been told that this
isn't our only future.
Huh?
They said we have many futures
and this is just
one possibility.
What are you talking about?
Is this our future or not?
It's difficult to understand,
but there are
countless dimensions
which co-exist in every
second of our time.
So that's why this is one
of many possible futures.
[YU] So there're...
many possible futures?
That's what Ai told me.
Huh? Why would
she tell you that?
I mean the Ai of this world.
Of this world?!
[LILY]
Hey, you're here again?!
And you got a man with you.
Lily!
It's a mini-Miho!
[LILY]
I'm Lily! Miho's my mom!
[YU]
Oh.
You're kind of... dumb.
I mean, seriously, don't you
know the Dragon Soldiers
are all out looking for you?
I know that, but I didn't
have a choice in the matter.
I was brought here somehow.
Jeez, you sound like it's
no big deal. Well, it is!
Ugh! They'll catch you!
Yes, they will!
They'll try to put me
in that fish tank again!
I got it! Yes!
Let's go to Auntie's!
[BOTH]
Who's "Auntie"?
Haruka! But I don't--
What happened, what's going on?!
I'm not entirely sure.
I don't understand,
it's unbelievable...
Yu?!
That is your name, isn't it?
Uh, yes, ma'am.
[AMAMIKU]
It's been ages...
You're still 12
years old, right?
I am.
I don't think this is really
Ai; she's way too nice.
[AMAMIKU]
Quickly. Let's get you inside.
You don't want to be spotted
by the Dragon Soldiers.
[LILY]
Hurry! Hurry!
[MIHO]
Wow, this is totally amazing!
[ISAMI]
You really think this'll work?
[AI]
They can hear you!
Karasu, stand right below it.
How's this?
Stay still for a minute.
Looks like we're ready to go.
[ISAMI] I still don't
think it's got a chance.
Now. Activate.
[ATORI]
Is it working?
It's no good.
What's wrong?
There's not enough power.
Get some!
Don't stop, try it again!
Why isn't it working?
Kosagi.
[KOSAGI]
Use this.
What?
A storage battery.
Hey, where did you
get this thing?
[KOSAGI]
Kuina gave it to me.
Kosagi...
I'm certain I won't
be needing it.
Be sure they both
come back, Karasu.
[AMAMIKU] They performed a
fixed-reverse calculation
on your location.
[YU]
I think I remember Tobi
saying something
along those lines.
[HARUKA]
Oh, great, more confusing stuff.
It doesn't matter
how you got here,
we just have to find a way
to get you both home.
Where's Karasu?
It's up to me to
protect Haruka now.
I made a deal about
it with Karasu.
Yes, I see. It's imperative
that you keep her safe.
Yu, thanks.
Hang on. We're going to
have to go to that room
so we can get back, won't we?
[YU]
The room we landed in?
[AMAMIKU] That sounds like
the transporter room.
[YU] Then we should
go now, so we can--
[YU grunting]
Hey, I brought
food for everyone!
[HARUKA]
Yu!
[AMAMIKU]
What's wrong?!
I'll be okay...
[HARUKA]
Oh no!
Don't try to stand!
What's going on?
I feel so...
so weak and used up.
[HARUKA]
It's okay. Hang on.
[LILY] Oh no, why is
he glowing like that?
[HARUKA]
Please, no.
Haruka! Go outside, now!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
[AMAMIKU]
Hurry!
[HARUKA]
Why?! I wanna stay here! No!
[AMAMIKU] This isn't
something you should see!
Get back here!
He's not breathing!
[HARUKA]
Yu!
[OPERATOR]
What is this?
It can't be...
Haruka!
[HARUKA] Let go! Why won't
you let me inside?
[AMAMIKU] You need to
calm down... and listen to me!
[AMAMIKU]
Stop it!
Well, you're a pretty tough
girl, aren't you, Haruka?
[HARUKA]
Ai...
Just listen to me.
In our reality where the quantum
revolution has occurred,
all matter has lapsed
into a quantum state.
It is a world where the
existence of all dimensions
can not be established including
that of humanity itself.
[AMAMIKU] We are an unstable
existence, without an observer.
"Observer"?
So we stabilized this world
by transforming
everything into data.
We call this descriptive data
"Reizu" and it is stored inside
a massive quantum computer.
We named this world "La'cryma".
In other words, things
without a data description
cannot exist here.
That's why Yu is disappearing.
Then why isn't it
happening to me?!
Because you are a special case.
You were recorded in memory
the last time you came.
Can't be...
[AMAMIKU] Alright now, listen
to me, this is very important.
I know that it must
seem like Yu is dead.
But as long as his
existence remains unstable,
in the larger picture, his death
here is only theoretical.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
It's quite simply an
overlapping temporal state
of dimensions where he's dead,
and dimensions where he's alive.
[HARUKA]
So he's dead... and alive?
[AMAMIKU]
Yes.
[HARUKA] So he's alive
in a different world.
That's right.
And that's why you
must not look at him now.
Since you're the Dragon Torque,
you may very well have the power
to finalize
whatever you observe.
[AMAMIKU] If you witness
him in a state of death now,
his death will
become a reality.
[HARUKA]
That... just can't be...
[AMAMIKU] However, if you can
witness him in a living state,
and both of you can recognize
each other's existences,
he will be reestablished
into a living state.
I'm sure of it.
Fine, then what dimension
is he alive in right now?
[AMAMIKU]
I don't know.
[KUINA]
He's in Shangri-la.
[YU]
Haruka...
What is this place?
Where the heck am I?
This isn't Heaven is it?
[YU]
Not again...
[NOEIN cackles] I never thought
you would come to this land.
That means even I wasn't
able to fully predict
the will of this dimension.
He's in Shangri-la?!
[AMAMIKU]
No, don't!
[KUINA] You want to save him?
Then come with me to Shangri-la!
Shangri-la?
Kuina! Why have you
betrayed La'cryma?!
[KUINA]
Hah! You have no right to speak
after aiding the
Dragon Torque's escape!
Now move!
Or are you going to help
Karasu, who killed Fukurou?
Liar! It wasn't him!
Please believe me.
It wasn't him.
He and Isami-- they were
best friends to the very end.
And Isami said he missed you.
He said that?
Karasu didn't kill him,
Noein did!
That's why I can't stand
Shangri-la! I hate it!
[HARUKA]
But...
Karasu!
Kuina! You will never have her!
[KUINA]
I've had enough of you!
[HARUKA] Please don't!
Yu is alive in Shangri-la,
and I have to go there
to save him, now!
I have to go!
Or else he's gonna die!
He's what?!
[LILY]
Auntie!
[AMAMIKU]
Lily!
[LILY]
Oh no! It's a monster!
[KUINA]
La'cryma is about to disappear.
It was just another
weak dimension.
Shangri-la isn't the only cause
for the dimensional
assimilation.
This is fate!
Those who are deemed unnecessary
are destined to disappear!
Karasu, you agree
with me, don't you?!
Born in this dimension,
have you ever once
felt the satisfaction
of existence?!
Nothing but pain and suffering!
Don't you know
that this dimension
is meant only to bring
misery for those
who exist in it?
And that is why only
Shangri-la can save me!
As long as I have
the Dragon Torque,
I will be accepted
into Shangri-la!
To a dimension
filled with happiness
where there's no suffering!
[YU]
Where am I?
[NOEIN]
This place is Shangri-la.
The blissful future that
the people wished for.
[YU] What people wished
for this? Where is everyone?
[NOEIN]
They have no form.
This is a world where
only consciousness exists.
Consciousness?
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
No, don't!
If I don't go, he's gonna die.
It's okay, Karasu,
I promise I'll save him.
[KUINA] Noein!
Accept me into Shangri-la!
[AMAMIKU]
Haruka!
That's the guy who
helped me and Isami.
[NOEIN] Yes, you are right.
You've met him once.
This is what Isami looks
like in fifteen years.
That's Isami?!
[NOEIN] But are you aware
that Isami was murdered?
And who was the culprit?
It was you!
You killed him.
You'll be killing him
fifteen years into the future!
[YU] Fifteen years in
the future? Karasu, you mean!
[NOEIN]
No, not him. It was me.
Because I am you.
In your future, you will
kill your best friend.
Not true! That's a lie! A lieee!
[KUINA laughs]
We have arrived!
The eternal Shangri-la!
This is it?
Why?!
This dimension...
Shangri-la is rejecting me!
[KUINA]
No! Aaah!
Karasu!
[KUINA] You're definitely
the man I made you out to be.
I knew you would make
a good Dragon Soldier.
So my judgment was
correct after all.
And now look at me.
This is what I get
for wishing for Shangri-la.
[KUINA] Laugh, Karasu!
Look at what a fool I am!
[KUINA laughing]
He's falling apart.
[YU screams]
Yu!
He's calling out to me!
[HARUKA]
He's in there.
[KARASU]
Hold on tight.
[KARASU yells]
Go!
[NOEIN] You will live
with infinite sorrow.
Now and forever until you die.
That is your dimension.
Yu! Karasu, hurry!
[NOEIN]
Huh? What?!
Hey!
Haruka!
[KARASU]
Dammit!
[NOEIN]
Get out of my way!
[HARUKA]
No, don't!
No!
Yu!
[HARUKA]
Hang in there!
Please, you gotta!
What?
No, no, what's going on?!
Karasu, where are you?!
[HARUKA]
He's disappearing! Help me!
Please don't go... Stay here...
Don't disappear!
Don't go...
[LILY]
He's disappearing!
Haruka... please let it
be that you found him.
[YU]
Haruka...
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Yu!
Give a guy a chance
to breath, will ya?
[HARUKA]
Thank Heaven!
Hey!
[HARUKA]
You're really here!
Okay, stop hugging me!
[HARUKA]
I'm just so happy!
[YU]
C'mon, let go of me already.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[TOBI]
Shangri-la is unstable.
There is a risk that
Haruka will disappear.
[ATORI]
Let's get moving here, shall we?
[NOEIN] You have made
the correct choice.
[HARUKA]
Next episode: "Illusion."
Will you be able to find it?