[YU]
Haruka!
Could that be...?
It's that guy!
Wha--?!
Hey, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Yu!
[HARUKA]
Are you okay?
Are you feeling any pain?
No, I'll be fine.
[YU]
Get away from her!
Yu!
Run! We have to get away!
[HARUKA] No, we don't.
It's okay. He saved my life.
Uh?
[HARUKA] Are you okay,
Karasu? Are you hurt?
[KARASU]
Don't worry. It's temporary.
I'll be just fine soon enough.
[HARUKA] No way! We can't
leave you like this.
Hey, Yu. Help me out here.
[YU]
You're out of your mind.
[HARUKA]
Yu?
Yu!
Ugh, what's his problem anyway?
So, are you sure you're-- Oh!
[HARUKA] Oops... I can't go
around looking like this...
How am I gonna get home?
[FUKURO] I can't believe him...
Damn you, Karasu.
That fool has even
severed his pipeline
to protect the Dragon Torque.
His betrayal will
not be tolerated.
We will kill him ourselves.
That damned fool...
He knows damn well that
she's not the same Haruka...
Did you find her?
I asked around.
Nobody's seen her.
I knew it! Haruka's been taken
to a completely
different Universe!
A place populated by people
equipped with science
far superior to our own!
--Shove a sock in it, Miho.
--[MIHO] Hmph!
What should we do, Ms. Yukie?
Well, we should
probably start by
rechecking all of the places
she might've gone to.
Sounds good!
Hey, I think you should
get into the backseat.
Yeah? Why should I?
[ISAMI]
Huh?
Because he really wants
to sit next to Ms. Yukie.
What?! No, I don't! Shut up!
[phone ringing]
Yu, what's goin' on?
[YU]
Haruka is back.
[ISAMI] What?! Are you
serious?! Where is she?
[YU] Don't worry. She's with
someone she trusts...
[ISAMI]
What are you talking about?
[YU]
I-I gotta go.
Hey, are you still there?
What's wrong?
[YUKIE]
Has he found Haruka yet?
[ISAMI]
That's what he said.
That's great.
I am totally gonna rip
Haruka a new one for this!
[phone ringing]
[ASUKA]
Yes, Kaminogi residence?
Oh, hello, Ai.
[AI]
Um, is Haruka home yet?
I'm not really sure.
Hang on a sec, I'll check.
[ASUKA] Haruka, it's
for you, honey. Haruka?
Oh, uh... Um...
I'll be right back.
Hey, that's cool.
[KARASU grunts]
[ASUKA]
Huh?
Hey, are you up there, Haruka?
Uh...
[thudding]
Oh, what now.
[HARUKA] Hide here, okay?
I'll be back later.
[ASUKA]
Haruka, can you hear me?
I'm home! I'm right here!
Why don't you answer me
when I call you?
[HARUKA] Sorry. I've had
a lot on my mind...
There's a phone call
for you from Ai.
It's Ai...?
Hey, Ai, where've you been?
[AI]
That's what I'd like to know!
We've looked everywhere
for you! Where have you been?!
Yeah! Were you implanted with
an alien mind control device?!
[HARUKA] Hey, listen,
Ai, will you tell me
--what day and time it is?
--[AI] Huh?
How long has it been
since I went missing?
[AI]
About three hours.
Three hours?
[AI]
What's wrong? Are you okay?
[BARON barking]
What's the matter, Baron?
Ahhh... I have to go now!
[AI]
Hey--!
Are you hiding something?
What would I be hiding?
You sneaked something
in the house, didn't you?
You're acting suspicious!
No, that's not true!
[ASUKA] Every time you
bring something home,
you always hide it in here.
[HARUKA]
What? No I don't!
Don't go in there!
That's strange...
There's nothing in here.
See, I told you there was
nothing in here, didn't I?
[ASUKA] Well... I could've
sworn I heard something...
[HARUKA]
Now are you satisfied?
[HARUKA gasps]
And by the way...
Huh?
What is up with that
outfit you're wearing?
Uh... I'm gonna be in a play
with Ai and everyone else!
This is the costume!
What do you think? Like it?
[ASUKA]
Hmm...
It looks good on you!
[HARUKA]
Hehe, yeah!
[HARUKA] Baron, you keep this
a secret from Mom, okay?
[BARON whines]
I don't get it.
They told me I've
only been missing
for around three hours...
How is that possible?
Because I'm positive I was
in that world longer.
You leapt between
time and space...
I did?
[HARUKA gasps]
[BARON whines]
I should change.
[YU gasps]
You will not leave this house
through the window again.
You are not some
kind of cat burglar.
What on earth have
you been doing?
Don't make me
worry anymore...
Go back to the
good boy you were.
Don't!
This is my future,
not yours! I'll decide...
...my own life, okay?!
No, you won't!
[MIYUKI]
It doesn't work that way!
Where are you going?!
Yu, come back here right now!
Let go!
[MIYUKI sobs]
[MIYUKI]
Why... Why won't you listen...?
Why do you hate me so much...?
Yu...!
[MIYUKI sobs]
[BOY A] We'll treat
you guys! No worries!
[GIRL A] That's great,
'cause we're broke!
[BOY B] You're in luck,
'cause he's got some money!
[phone ringing]
[MIYUKI]
Hello?
Oh, it's you, dear.
[MIYUKI] Yes. So you'll be
staying at the office tonight...
I see...
No, it's not a problem at all.
Yes, Yu is doing fine.
Okay, bye.
[MIYUKI growls]
[ATORI] I'm exhausted...
I'm so damn tired...
[TOBI]
Well, complaining won't help,
so you might as well
get used to it.
[ATORI]
Oh, shut up. I'm so lethargic.
[TOBI] Let's try to
find something to eat.
[TOBI] Hey, Atori. This looks
like it's still edible.
I'm not gonna eat that crap.
Hey, we really need to get
some kind of nutrition
in us right away!
[ATORI]
Agh, this is pathetic!
Without our pipelines attached,
we're reduced to bottom
feeders in this world.
[TOBI]
It's the best we can hope for.
At least we don't have
withdrawal symptoms.
[ATORI] They fed me a line of
crap about altering every cell
in my body on a quantum level
to make me stronger,
then poked and prodded
me for this?!
And now I'm gonna die
in this depressing dump.
Eventually, the effects
of Shangri-la
will spread to
this dimension, too.
And any way you look at it,
it's all going to hell.
[ATORI chuckles]
[ATORI sighs]
What's with those guys?
They're weak now.
Oh yeah...
[ATORI]
Tobi! Get me water! Find some!
[TOBI]
Alright.
I've found some, Atori.
[HARUKA sighs]
[knocking]
[HARUKA] Are you awake,
Karasu? I'm coming in.
Morning. How are
you feeling today?
Are you doing a
little bit better?
Don't you worry.
I'm doing a lot better now.
[HARUKA] Are you hungry?
Is there anything special
you like to eat?
I'll bring it to you.
I do not require much
food to sustain my body.
But I do need water
if you have some.
Seriously? All you
want is water?
Yeah, that is all. Thanks.
Kay. I'll bring you
some water. Just sit tight.
[HARUKA] How did you
get the name "Karasu"?
[KARASU] In our world, after you
have completed your training
to become a soldier, you are
honored with a new name.
Karasu was the name
that was given to me.
[HARUKA]
I see.
Karasu? Is it true
that your world
is really one of our futures?
That's right. In fact,
it's a parallel universe.
[HARUKA]
Oh...
[KARASU]
Is it difficult to believe?
No, it's not that, I guess.
I mean, I think that woman
really was my friend, Ai.
And...
Are you concerned about...
your own future?
Not really... I don't think
about it at all that much.
But can I ask you something?
In the past... was your name Yu?
And why do you think that?
It's just a hunch.
[KARASU]
I see...
Haruka. I am merely an
illusion in this dimension.
It does not really
matter who I am.
[HARUKA]
I understand.
It makes sense.
You are who you are.
[BARON barks]
[HARUKA] What's the matter,
Baron? Is someone there?
[HARUKA]
Yu!
[HARUKA] Hey! You're up
pretty early this morning!
Here, you forgot this.
Right... It fell off. Thank you.
Did something... happen between
you and your mom again?
[YU]
What do you care?
Don't talk to me like that!
We've all been worried
sick about you!
Just forget about it! I slept
in the park last night, okay?!
I'm not going back
home anymore. See ya.
Hey, Yu! Hold on
a second, will ya?
What d'you want?!
Just come with me, alright?
Hey, what're you doin'?!
[EMI]
Miyuki, what're you doing?
Oh, I guess you're
still eating, huh?
I have practice this morning,
so I'm going without you.
Don't be late for school now!
Oh, Emi...
Yu... Oh, I just
have to find him...
[MIYUKI]
Hm?
[YU]
What the hell do you want?
[HARUKA] Oh, come on.
Have you eaten anything?
[BARON whines]
Hey, Baron. Long time no see.
Hey, cut it out! Hey!
[YU laughs]
[YU]
Come on, boy!
Oh, Baron.
You're such a big moose.
[YU]
Ooh, I'll get you for that!
[YU laughs]
So, tell me what's wrong.
What happened, Yu?
Just forget about me.
Where were you?
Huh?
We spent the entire
night looking for you.
I'm fine! You guys
shouldn't worry about me!
Well, we did!
[HARUKA] Anyway!
What happened with you?
Did you really spend the
whole night in the park?
I said that's none
of your business.
[HARUKA]
You did. But we promised
to run away together, remember?
Yeah, right.
You're the one who forgot.
I promise you I didn't
forget. I just--
I don't need your excuses, 'kay?
[HARUKA gasps]
Right, boy? You'll agree
with me, won't ya?
[BARON whines]
[ASUKA] I guess Haruka
must still be sleeping.
So, what're you gonna do now?
Your mom's gotta be pretty
worried about you...
Just keep your nose
outta my business.
Y'know, if you don't wanna
take the entrance exams,
you should just tell her.
Don't you think I would've
done that if it was that easy?
Huh?
She wasn't always like this.
You know what I mean?
She'd tell me to study
and get good grades,
but she's not the same now.
Didn't it all start
about two years ago, huh?
Around there, yeah. Probably
started around the same time
my grandma in Sapporo died.
[YU gasps]
That's right! Mom did
something weird on the train
coming home from the funeral...
[MIYUKI] Mother... Are you
happy to see her again?
You loved Emi. She really
was such a great sister.
I'll miss her.
So, who's Emi?
She probably meant my aunt.
I never really got
a chance to meet her.
Why not?
She passed away. I was
told that she was killed
in a really bad car accident
when she was still
in high school.
Oh no... That's so sad...
I wonder why your mom would
say something like that?
Ah, beats me.
I'm kinda hungry...
Oh, you want me to
get you something?
[YU] D'you still keep munchies
in your desk drawer?
I'll just have that.
Hey! Get outta there!
Don't go through people's
desks without asking!
[YU] You haven't got anything
important in here.
[HARUKA]
Hey, cut it out!
[YU]
See? Found some.
[HARUKA]
That's my chocolate!
If you're hungry, I'll just
go get you something to eat!
[YU] Y'know, you've always
been a skinny, little kid.
But if you keep eating
junk food like this...
...you're gonna get real fat.
You haven't changed at all
either, have you?! Give it back!
[thudding]
What in the world could
she be doing up there
with Baron so early
in the morning?
[HARUKA]
I said give it back!
[YU]
I don't think so!
[HARUKA]
Yu, cut it out! Quit it!
[YU]
Junkie! Junkie!
Don't call me that!
[BARON barks]
[HARUKA]
Huh?
What is it, Baron?
[YU]
Hey, what's up?
Mom...
She's come here looking for you.
Tell her I'm not here!
Don't let her find me!
But what if she finds out
that you are here?
I know! Here!
[YU]
Hey, where are we going?
You can hide in this room.
Karasu is in here, too.
Huh? What're you doing?
Why are you here?
[knocking]
[HARUKA]
Coming! I'll be right there!
What do I do now? This is
really not too good...
[knocking]
[HARUKA]
Coming! Just give me a second!
Sorry to drop by so early today.
Yu, are you here?
He's not here.
[MIYUKI] I know he's in here!
Get out of my way!
No! Please, don't do this!
Thought so!
Come in.
[KARASU] What's the matter?
Are you afraid?
Do it!
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
Yu! Come out here, now!
[KARASU]
You're such a spineless coward!
[YU] You don't know anything
about me, do you?!
[HARUKA]
Next episode, "Beyond Time."
Do you remember the old days?