Whoa. What in the
hell is that thing?
Oh no, it's disappearing.
What's wrong with me?
I really am going mental.
Dammit.
Oh, Yu...
[HARUKA gasps]
What is that?!
[HARUKA]
Yu, hurry!
We have to leave here!
[HARUKA gasps]
Hello.
It's him...
[ATORI cackles]
[ATORI] You two,
together again. How cute.
[YU]
Let's go!
[ATORI]
That's enough.
Don't waste my time.
Stay back!
Stay away! Stay away!
You know you're
really pissing me off.
Well that explains it.
Imagine that...
running into the Karasu
of this dimension.
You wouldn't really wanna
cut me, would ya?
[YU whimpers]
Something like this?
[ATORI cackling]
[YU whimpering]
[YU screams]
[ATORI cackling]
What's the matter?
Are you done already?
Damn I hate children.
They're so annoying
and tiresome.
[YU yelps]
Yu!
Should I crush you?
Does that feel good?
[HARUKA]
Stop it! You're hurting him!
[ATORI gasps]
[ATORI]
I know those eyes.
You do possess the same
eyes that he does.
Those are the eyes that
infuriate my soul!
[ATORI groaning]
Not again...
Time for all Karasus in
every dimension... to perish.
No!
[ATORI groaning]
[HARUKA] Yu! It's working!
Come on, let's go!
[HARUKA]
Hurry! Hurry!
Yu!
We still don't have complete
stability in this dimension.
[HARUKA]
So why's he after you?
[YU]
I don't know.
This doesn't make sense.
Why would anyone wanna kill me?
Who was that guy anyway?
He isn't even human.
[HARUKA]
So then...
What's that?
Do you hear that?
[banging]
What's that noise?
[YU, HARUKA gasp]
Look at the ceiling!
Haruka, hold on!
Huh?
[HARUKA, YU scream]
[YU panting]
Haruka, are you alright?
Yeah, Yu, I think I am.
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
It's that guy again...
Yeah, you're right.
[ATORI]
You again?
Karasu... always taking credit
for other people's hard work.
Your glory days are over.
Starting right now.
[KARASU gasps]
Time to die.
[YU, HARUKA yelp]
Bad boy.
You should not be using
Reizu to shield yourself.
[ATORI] You almost let
the Dragon Torque fall.
[ATORI cackles]
[KARASU grunts]
[KARASU groans]
[ATORI cackles]
Ha!
[YU]
This isn't good.
It's the end.
We're all gonna die.
[YU]
It's hopeless. We're done for!
[KARASU]
Shut up!
If you don't wanna die,
then fight!
Yu!
I can't do it, okay? I can't.
You are so pathetic.
Is that all you're
good at? Giving up?
Come on, you coward!
Show me some guts!
I can't. I'm too scared.
[ATORI grunting]
[KARASU groaning]
I'm going to die now.
Then die!
[KARASU] Anyone who won't
fight for their life should die!
Is that all you've got?
I expected more from you.
[ATORI] I've always hated
that look on your face.
It makes me want to vomit.
[KARASU gasps]
[ATORI gasps]
[KARASU grunting]
[YU, HARKU screaming]
[ATORI yelling]
Yu...
Are you okay, Haruka?
Uh... Yu... you're bleeding.
The reading has disappeared.
Are you sure that's right?
Maybe you should check it again.
Maybe you're mistaken.
We could just head back.
--It's getting' kinda late.
--It's not a mistake.
I am absolutely sure
the source is here...
[UCHIDA]
...somewhere on this mountain.
[HARUKA]
Doesn't it hurt?
[YU] No, it's fine.
It's not bleeding anymore.
[HARUKA]
Are you sure you're alright?
Would you please stop
asking me that?
[HARUKA] But your head...
and I'm sure that your feet
must be bothering you too.
[YU]
Would you quit buggin' me?
You can be so stubborn.
[HARUKA]
Hey, here's the road!
[YU]
Haruka!
[HARUKA]
We made it!
[YU]
Haruka!
[KOORIYAMA, UCHIDA gasp]
[KOORIYAMA]
What the...
So lucky!
[YU]
Haruka, are you crazy?
Excuse me, sir.
Could you please give us a ride
down to the bottom
of the mountain?
[KOORIYAMA]
Huh?
[HARUKA gasps]
Wait, I know you.
Huh?
[OPERATOR]
Can you hear me?
[ATORI groans]
[OPERATOR] One bird has
returned to the hen house.
[KUINA] Damn Atori.
He's certainly wreaked
his share of havoc.
I didn't imagine that he'd be
forcefully retrieved
because of an irregularity.
[FUKURO] Kuina, what about
the Dragon Torque?
There's no need
for us to panic, Fukuro.
The bigger danger is that
we're leaving our marks
here in this dimension.
The strain of our presence here
is already starting to show.
First and foremost, we must
erase all proof of
our existence here.
Then we need to locate Karasu.
And obliterate every trace...
[KUINA groans]
[TOBI] Kuina!
[KUINA] It's fine. The leg
teleported back. Move on.
It appears that my body...
is not entirely compatible
with this dimension.
[MIYUKI] Did you really think
I would believe that?
Why were you out on the street
at this time of night?
I feel ashamed
to be your mother.
You are absolutely forbidden
from leaving this house
except for cram school.
And I will take you to and
from that school myself.
[HARUKA]
And then the light flew around.
What do you think it was?
[ASUKA]
Hey, hold still.
Well, you're bound to run into
things like that if you go
wandering around
at this time of night.
Ow.
[ASUKA]
Okay, all done.
And remember, summer break
doesn't mean you can
run around outside
at all hours.
So you don't believe me?
Huh?
[HARUKA]
I'm not lying, you know.
Haruka, I used to fantasize
a lot back when I was your age.
I wished for something
exciting and magical
to happen almost everyday, too.
But I'm not lying about this.
Forget it. I'm going
to take a bath.
[HARUKA] That man's name
was Karasu, right?
I wonder if he's gonna be okay.
[HARUKA sighs]
[phone ringing]
[ASUKA]
Hey, it's me.
[UCHIDA]
Those children we picked up
didn't appear to be lyin' to us.
But there are no signs of
destruction anywhere, right?
Well, would you stop
worrying about it?
Just relax for a minute and
enjoy the view of the city.
[TOBI] The restoration of the
demolished space was successful.
It's perfect for us.
[FUKURO]
Kosagi, have you located Karasu?
[KOSAGI]
I have a reading, but I can't
lock down his coordinates.
[FUKURO] But is he still
in this dimension?
Yes. Of that I am certain.
He may be very weak.
I think that's why
his coordinates may be
difficult to ascertain.
Ahh! Stop it! Stay back!
Dragon Torque! Stay back!
[VOICE 1]
He's become deranged.
[VOICE 3] He must be
returned to full strength.
[VOICE 2] Surgery is risky
with this type of derangement.
[VOICE 3]
The Juoh Kai is demanding.
There will always be risks.
[VOICE 1] So, this is all
for the absolute coordinates?
[ATORI] If it comes...
If it comes La'cryma...
La'cryma will be...
...completely obliterated!
No! No, stop it!
I don't wanna die!
Stop! Stop!
Don't take me away! No!
[MIHO] I can't find any mention
of it in the newspaper.
I looked and looked.
[HARUKA]
That is so weird.
[MIHO] It's not on the radio
or television news either,
and I haven't seen anything
about it on the internet.
I surfed this morning.
[AI] And anyway... the ropeway
looks fine to me.
Yeah, that's the thing.
You know what? When you were
young, I remember you used to
freak about about
seeing things too.
What? Ghostly visions?
[HARUKA]
It wasn't like that.
And it wasn't that long ago that
I stopped seeing those things.
[AI] By the way...
why was that ghost after Yu?
I guess I'm not
really certain why.
But it attacked him
the other night as well.
[MIHO] What?
[AI] The other night?
Oh yeah. After we got
separated at the graveyard.
Haruka, you were alone
in the graveyard
that entire time with Yu?
[AI]
Hey... are you two going out?
Huh? No, no, no, you're wrong!
We're not dating or anything.
I swear to you that we're just
childhood friends, that's it.
If you're not dating Yu,
then what were you doing?
I mean, why were you
alone with him?
Nothing in particular really...
[MIHO]
That's not fair, Haruka!
Huh?
You can't have him, he's mine!
I've had a crush on him
for a long time!
[HARUKA, AI yelp]
[MIHO] Oh, what a shock.
I don't think I'll recover.
[AI]
What? Are you serious, Miho?
It just breaks my heart. But I
guess I could let you have him
all to yourself...
because we're such good friends.
It's really not
like that at all.
There's only one choice.
I'll move on
and find someone else to love.
That's great! Spoken like
a true best friend.
You can do it, Miho!
Yeah!
[MIYUKI] Please do not see
my son for the time being.
[MIYUKI]
I'm sure you understand.
This is an
important time for him.
[HARUKA]
U-Um...
[MIYUKI]
Goodbye.
[HARUKA]
Oh...
Yu...
[HARUKA gasps]
[YU grunts]
[HARUKA groans]
[YU gasps]
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
Huh?
Where am I?
I know this place...
[YU] One... two... three...
four... five... six...
[HARUKA] I used to play here
with Yu when we were little.
[HARUKA gasps]
[KARASU grunting]
[HARUKA]
Ka-Karasu?
Are you the one who called
me here to this place?
Please, I need some water.
Now.
[HARUKA gasps]
[KARASU]
Get me some water.
Get water.
[HARUKA]
Here you go.
Um, would you like more, Karasu?
Alright, I'll go
get some more then.
[HARUKA gasps]
Uh...
Let's go together... Haruka.
You're after Yu again?
Well done, Karasu.
Yes, you managed to capture
the Dragon Torque.
Wait, who is the Dragon Torque?
[KARASU]
Yu has never been our target.
Huh?
You're the one.... Haruka.
[HARUKA]
I'm dreaming again...
That summer day's dream.
[KUINA]
Noein, why are you here?
Haruka will
eventually disappear.
I hate you, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Next: "Friends."
Don't cry.