Well, how 'bout it...?
Are you guys free later?
Hmm...?
You mean tonight?
Mm-hmm!
Not real sure yet...
Depends on how
theater club goes.
Ah, ay, ee...
Shouldn't be
a problem, though...
There is this area I've
been wanting to check out,
if you think you
guys're up for it.
Fine by me.
You in, Eri?
I don't know.
I've got a lot
of studying to do...
I think I could maybe
meet up after ten.
That's what I like to hear...!
You can only do
so much studying...
A girl's gotta live a little!
Tonight it is, then!
We'll meet in Mac Anu at ten.
Show up late and you shall
be left for the enemy!
Excuse me?
Thought I was the dramatic one.
Dammit...
Hello?!
I could use a little
help here, you guys!
Nice move!
Well, this is getting old quick.
More of 'em?
Smoke Screen!
Hold on!
Wait for me!
That's our Tobias,
always good in a pinch!
We're lucky to
have you for a friend!
Flattery will get
you nowhere, Sakuya.
Look at you,
suddenly all bashful...!
You were great, too, Mary.
Thanks!
Jeez...
You got lost on a straight
path...? How'd you manage that?
It's not like
you're some newbie.
Yes!
But even a monkey
may fall from a tree.
Even Shakespeare himself
may mangle a verse!
Yeah...
You're no Shakespeare.
Give her a break...
You know the old saying,
"Even death won't cure a fool."
Our dear Miss Sakuya
here definitely falls
in that category.
Real nice...!
Don't wound me physically,
just hurt my pride instead!
"Pride," she says...
Yeah, that's right...!
Now knock it off or
I'll hurt you for real!
Wow!
I didn't know you could
get through this way!
Yeah...
The place has a bit of
history to it, in fact.
Oh.
What kind of history?
Something special?
It's an occult spot, but nothing
ventured, nothing gained...
And it's at least worth trying.
If we take this secret route,
the treasure chest
prize changes.
Even better, this way we get
to avoid the boss fight!
We're not going to fight...?
Wouldn't it be better to get
the experience poi--Hey, wait!
Sweet!
I found an item!
Sakuya!
Uh, yeah?
You're always stopping
to pick up some lame item.
No wonder you got los-
Everyone take your positions!
What're they doing?
Impressive--looks
like one of the guilds
is gonna fight this boss.
That dragon's huge!
The One Sin.
The World's
unbeatable monster...
This thing's the
stuff of legend...
In terms of raw power,
it has no rival...
The first players in history to
defeat it were given a name...
Descendants of Fianna.
Let's see how they do.
She's um...
Nerding out?
It has Reflect...
We'll target the elemental hits,
just like we planned...
Healing team, stand back
at a safe distance.
They're actually going to
attack the dragon head-on.
This is so hardcore...!
I need a screenshot!
Don't get lost this time!
It's going to breathe fire!
Everybody spread out!
Healing team, move in the
second it runs out of breath!
Whoa, its breath
is lasting crazy long!
What's that?
I kind of stepped
on something...
What do I do now?!
Please!
Can't you stand still
for two seconds?
I think it stopped.
Any static?
None detected.
Was that just an event?
No way.
So what now?
It'll breathe fire again.
Get outside!
This boss fight has a
surprise instant-kill trap...
They've got us.
Look over there!
That's Tobias the
information broker.
I doubt it'll chase us
all the way here.
Seriously?!
Thanks, CC Corp...
Let's go!
Mary, what--?!
We're done for if it
breathes fire at us here!
She's got spunk.
Come back!
You idiot!
I was leading the
thing away from you!
What're you doing?!
If Tobi and I just run away,
how are you going to escape?
Get over here!
Let's run.
Hurry!
Man, I thought we
were dead for sure!
And whose fault
do you think that was?
I mean, we didn't
even get the rare item...
We went through all that
trouble for nothing.
No, that's not true.
It was a game...
but regardless,
everything we did tonight
was a real experience...
As far as I'm concerned, the
memories we make in The World
are worth far more than
any treasure could be.
Tobias...
Hey, when'd you pick up that
rare mantle you're wearing?
Huh...?
Hey, yeah, that's new!
Well, memories are great,
but treasure's still awesome.
And here I was, all moved
by your little speech.
Y'gotta admit though,
tonight really was a blast.
Oh, yeah...
Awesome!
I love The World!
Asumi...?
Asumi!
Wake up already!
Yeah, I'm up.
I promise.
Eri's already here.
No way!
I'm so late!
Why didn't you
wake me up earlier?
Since you're going out
after school anyway,
pick up some tissues
for us, will you?
Huh?
How did you know
I was going out?
Hey!
I thought I told you not to
look through my stuff!
'Kay, later, Mom!
Sorry, Eri.
Let's book it!
Jeez...
why do you
oversleep every morning?
What I want to know
is why you don't.
You stay up as late as I do!
It's called an alarm?
Mine doesn't work before noon.
Uh-huh.
Hey, wait for us!
No, please come back...!
Stop the bus!
Please, we need to get on!
Look, Eri, I did it...!
Come on, hurry up!
We made it.
What, did you guys
run all the way here...?
You might try
waking up earlier.
Thanks...
What are you wearing?
You look like a freak.
Yeah, so what if I do...?
This may surprise you, but I
dress for utility and comfort.
Well, here in the
real world, anyway.
Blech...
It doesn't make sense to me.
When we're in-game,
your appearance is your
highest priority...
but then at school,
you don't even care if
you're dressed like a loser?!
I didn't ask for your opinion.
All right, today we'll be
talking about "implants."
As you know, this term
refers to the microchips
you all have inside of you...
We'll begin by examining why
this technology became
necessary, and the reason...
The price of materials has
been plummeting for days now.
There's info coming in
on a complete-item drop
in the new mission next month...
Guess I'd better sell
before demand dries up.
A 300,000 GP bounty?
It says here you're "charged
with malicious interference
and the consequent interruption
of a mission, as well as...
the deaths of sixteen guild
members." Sounds pretty serious.
"Contact Yata-no-Kagami guild...
Will pay for any info."
I'm officially finished.
Well, congrats...!
What will you do with your
newly-found celebrity?
You might take
this more seriously.
I'm not the only one
they're after, you know...
This is an absolute disaster.
How am I supposed to
live in The World now?
You know Asumi, this might
be a good opportunity
to take a little time
off from gaming.
With finals coming up and all.
Jeez, Eri, you sound like my mom
when you say stuff like that.
I'm just gonna pull an all-night
cramming session, so I'm good.
Oh, cool, then I'll do that too!
One night of studying
doesn't sound so bad.
You need to take
this seriously...!
Iori can get away with it
because she's got
better grades than you.
We're only a year away
from college entrance exams.
You're really not gonna
let this go, are you?
All I know is I'm not
playing The World
until finals are behind me...
We need to start
thinking about where
we're all going
to be a year from now.
That's easy.
In a year we'll all still
be playing The World together.
You're impossible!
I know what you meant...
The thing is, a year ago
I thought I'd just be
a high-schooler
like everyone else.
Study, take tests, and graduate.
But since I started
playing The World,
my life is about more
than just coming here
and then going home again...
It's like I suddenly realized
I can have a whole life
outside of school.
Sure, bad things happen,
like this stuff with the guild.
But that's only once in a while.
Mostly it's fun.
What I like most
is the companionship...
I met you because of
The World, Iori...
and Eri, I love that you and I
can play together
like when we were kids.
But I seem to be causing
lots of problems lately.
At the rate I'm going,
you guys'll get sick of me.
So I decided the most
important thing to me
was going to the
same college as Eri,
and I came up with a way
to make that happen.
Really?!
You did?
Yep.
And the solution is so simple
I can't believe I didn't
think of it before...
All right!
I expect to see the two of you
at our usual spot
at eight o'clock sharp.
What about this big plan
you came up with?
You'll see when you get there!
Somehow I doubt she's actually
put much thought into this.
Her solution's probably to do
all our studying in The World...
Eh?
Attention players:
This field is about to be shut
down for server maintenance--
Stop there!
You got the wrong person!
All because of
this stupid bounty.
I can't believe Mary and Tobias
aren't coming into
The World today.
This is boring.
I told them I wanted us
to study in-game.
We had a plan.
Maybe the guild would
forgive me if I apologized.
Whoa!
I got something...!
And it's heavy...!
This is gonna be a big one!
Find her?
Huh-uh.
Maybe she warped already.
I got someone watching the gate.
There must be somewhere
we haven't searched yet.
Move it.
Okay.
Wow, you really got yourself.
Seems like stuff in The World's
been a lot more realistic
than it has to be lately, huh?
Someone's taking
their job too seriously.
There, all done.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, o'course, no problem...
My name's Asu--uh...
Sakuya...
Nice to meet you!
You too.
I'm Hermit.
Hermit, huh...?
Like the tarot card?
Sort of...
So, I saw there's a big
bounty out on your head, huh?
Yeah!
Wait, you're not
with the guild, are you?!
No, don't worry.
But I was there and
saw all of that happen...
I wondered though,
did you happen to pick up
anything strange there?
Lemme think here...
Well...
I pick up pretty much anything
I see, so it's hard to say...
Was it a rare item or something?
No, never mind.
Forget it...
One other thing, though.
Those two who were
with you yesterday...
Are they coming back today?
Oh, you mean Tobias and Mary...
Not today, but I'll totally
introduce you to 'em sometime...
They're the friends I do
all my gaming with.
Your friends?
There she is!
Someone posted this
in the guild's name
and I want to know who!
I did not authorize this...
It's just shameless harassment!
I'm sorry, Ma'am, it was one of
the non-members who joined us.
I want this post pulled before
it causes us any trouble.
Do I make myself understood?
Uh...
What now?!
I, uh...
I'm terribly sorry to have
to inform you of this...
But his...
sympathizers have
already taken action.
Ow, that...
doesn't hurt.
Don't struggle...
Those restraints
are cheat items.
You ain't never
gettin' free of 'em.
And don't even think about
logging out with them on.
Try that crap and your
account will be forfeit.
Here's the deal:
you want me to let you go,
you better call the others
who were with you--
No way...!
I told you, I was the one
who activated the trap.
And I only made friends
with Hermit here a minute
before you captured us.
So there's no reason to drag
him into this, okay...?
It's not as simple as that...
Do you have any clue
how much time I spent
preparing for that quest?
How much work it took?
After all that, did you really
think I was gonna let you off
with nothin' but an apology?
Well...
yeah, I kinda did.
Not nice.
You're actin' like
we're the bad guys.
You're the one who started
all this, you know.
Come on...
one way or another,
you are gonna end up calling
those friends of yours.
We'll start with
this little guy.
Since you just met him,
I'm sure he's not as important
to you as the other two.
Whaddya think?
Filthy coward!
Leave my friends outta this!
Damn, she's taking
the offensive!
Sakuya!
Iyoten!
Hey, hold up a sec.
I can't tell one player
from another in this!
Iyoten, are you okay?
Find the girl, damn it.
Get off...!
Wait...
what was that?
My technique.
Ha!
They're here!
Don't worry,
Sakuya, I've gotcha!
No!
Everything under
control here, guys?
What, you're here too?!
What're you doing?
You guys told me earlier you
weren't gonna play today.
We had to swoop in to save
the damsel in distress.
We happened upon
an interesting post...
Imagine our surprise when
it said a wanted girl was
being chased through town.
Honestly, now's not the time
to go all doey-eyed.
Iyoten?
He was the free agent who joined
the battle against The One Sin.
Yes.
I looked into him,
and apparently he's got a record
of pulling stunts like this.
It was simple, really.
I just extracted the address
and reported it before we
came here to rescue you.
Wow, that was good thinking!
Piece o'cake.
I'm very sorry, Hermit.
You shouldnt've had to get
mixed up in our problems.
Oh...
it's fine.
Hey Hermit!
Thanks a lot for
saving me back there...
Catch.
It's just a little
thank-you present...
I know it's not much,
but it's the best I can
do at the moment, so...
Look!
Over there!
I see 'em!
Ugh, they found us already!
They're not gonna
give up easy, are they?
Those fools...
Move!
Right!
Ow!
Whoa, sorry!
Good, there's a Smoke Screen.
Quick, go around!
Dangit, these guys are stubborn.
You there!
I need to speak with you...!
Get down here this instant!
That's not good.
Just ignore her!
I think that little
girl's the boss.
Forget about her!
You ain't gettin' away!
Damn!
I surrender!
Asta!
Oh, yeah.
I'm way ahead of you.
Sakuya!
She needs help!
Hermit!
I think I'm gonna PK
you first, cat boy.
Please, no!
Stop right there!
Hermit, no!
What the--?!
What is this...?
Where are we?
It's certainly not
an official field.
Hey, you're that boss girl!
Where did all the others go?
Wait, are those...
people?
What?!
Sophia...?
Sakuya!
Hurry...!
We need to log out now...
This place is bad!
Mary...!
Tobias...!
But where'd Hermit go?
Don't know...
If he was PK'd
he'll return to town...
but for now--
Mary, just leave him!
Smith, no!
What happened?
I was caught unprepared...
This entire area...
It's a Pariah Folder.
Wait, what are you saying?
Come on.
Son of a...
What the heck was that?
I wish I knew...
but it can wait for now.
Let's just get offline quick.
'Kay.
I'll send an email later.
Behind you!
Take that!
Mary!
What's happening?!
Eri!
Comas...
Lost Ones...
past...
present...
legends...
facts...
personal information...
ghosts...
Password cracking...
implant chips...
investigations...
cover-ups...
destruction.
On the next episode...
of .hack//Quantum.