You're what we might call
a "Partial Lost One."
You're still being
displayed by the program,
but part of your data is lost.
It was most likely
taken to the other side,
when you tried
to help your friend.
That would also explain your
tingling hand in real life.
Speaking of, I was told
there's been some change
in your friend's condition.
Yeah...
On the night of the eleventh,
she responded just for a moment.
Which means it really was her
who we ran into in Mac Anu.
If our mysterious enemy
wants to do the most damage,
he'll target this
upcoming Territory War...
That's tens of thousands
of people from multiple
servers participating.
We can't shut down an event
that big on mere suspicion.
And of course, for the
admins it's business as usual.
How come?
It was such a major incident!
The trouble was localized,
though--and it didn't last long.
Do not log back in
until we've established
some countermeasures
against our foe.
I mean it, Sakuya.
Huh?!
You're what he's after--
if he catches you,
we lose our trump card.
I urge you to
exercise restraint.
Whoever's at the root of all
this is looking for some kind
of donor to help
a sick little boy.
That boy died seven years ago,
at the age of ten...
But our enemy's been scouring
The World turning players
into Lost Ones, still looking
for someone compatible.
What we can't figure out
is why he needs a donor
for someone who's dead.
I was giving it some thought...
You think it's possible he
doesn't know that the boy died?
What?!
No!
I figured he just went
crazy because he found out
the boy had died!
The kid's been dead seven years.
There's no way he wouldn't know!
Let's call it a day.
Get some food,
take a bath, and crash.
Black balls...?
Wow, girl, nice catch
finding this post.
What do you think?
Are these like what we saw?
This is too vague
to know for sure...
Great.
Here again.
Dead seven whole years, and it
still hurts every single time.
All this PK'ing sucks.
Yeah, maybe we
should've joined in.
We could've plowed through
a hundred people, easy.
Yeah, killing a hundred people
in a fake world is so cool.
Excuse me?
You talkin' to me, kid?
So what if I am...?
Are you gonna PK me?
Hey!
Don't be such a jerk!
You think I won't PK you on this
airship, you're sorely mistaken.
This from someone too
scared to join a fake war.
I guess you won't learn
until you die for real!
Me, die?
What are you, stupid?
I'll PK you right here and--
What did you do to her?!
You like to PK people?
Allow me to...
return the favor in
heart-stopping fashion.
No trace of anything odd...
The fog...?
It hurts...
Whoa, dude...
Over-acting a bit, aren'tcha?
What's happening?!
Oh god, it hurts!
It hurts!
What the hell...?
Hey!
Taste my steel!
Damn it!
These are--!
C'mon, Iori, pick up...
So it's begun.
This is on your head.
Seems your client is
a real piece of work.
Now, tell me who
ordered that list!
Sorry, missy.
I got me a code of hon--ow!
Hey!
Dammit, that hurt!
Do not misunderstand.
This is no longer
a game we are playing.
There's something wrong,
why can't we log out?!
Be a man.
Quit your whining...!
Incoming!
Tobias!
Hey!
I saw her!
Eri is here!
Dammit!
Heads up!
Sakuya!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Pretend that didn't happen!
Let's run...!
Now's our chance!
Come on!
Why did you come back here?!
Because, Iori, you wouldn't
answer the phone!
What?!
The One Sin!
The bad guy's doing this, too?
He sure isn't holding back.
We'd better get going...
Sakuya is waiting for us.
What is that?!
Huh?
Clearly he's no longer concerned
about settling things quietly...
And now, we can't even log out
until we destroy that thing.
How ya gonna do that if we don't
even know where the hell it is?!
We'll let him show us
where it is...
Look...
He's pulling out all the
biggest toys in the nursery.
With that kind of power, why
bother stomping about like this?
If he insists on continuing
this childish behavior,
then when things
stop going his way,
he's sure to show his hand.
We'll just have to use...
the Crest Gun.
Huh?!
Please hurry...!
Let us in!
Guild master's quarters!
Right!
I can't fully analyze
the converted mnemonics.
Try reconverting using
different disassemblers.
The Crest Gun's disabled
for players, isn't it?
I'm stealing control back
from the SysAdmins.
I said no!
But...
we really need...
to see her!
Idiot!
Why did you come back?!
Because of Eri--
What part of restraint
do you not understa--?!
Oh, I get it now...
It all makes sense.
Given the ability
you just displayed,
it's safe to assume your
right hand has access rights
to the Pariah Folder...
Place your hand on the wall...
But hey...!
Don't erase anything!
I'm rewriting the data through
Sakuya's FMD and address.
Secret door...?
I've taken the data we need
from the Pariah Folder.
Bummer.
Everybody stopped
the war game already?
Lame...
Who thought the end
would be so boring?
Wish I coulda played
with Sakuya again though...
Why...
us?!
Why can't we warp outta here?!
The Chaos Gate's down!
Reopen the gate!
We'll move all survivors
over to the Crest Gun!
Wait, what?!
Y'mean you were the ones
who locked the gate?!
The average player would never
obey a complete stranger...
And I needed an army here...
Start guiding them through!
Everyone get to
the Chaos Gate...!
We can fix all this...!
But we need your help!
It's time for us to leave too.
Let's go.
Iori!
It's a message from Hermit!
He says Eri's in Megin Fi!
Huh?!
I gotta go!
Stop her!
Do not let Sakuya go alone!
Whoa there...!
I'm sorry!
Why are you doing this...?!
I have to rescue Eri!
Shut up...!
I'm going to send Tobias
to the Inverted City...
Listen: even if you
find Eri in Megin Fi,
you can't do anything for her.
So I need you to
draw out our foe.
You're going to be
attacking Mag Mell's heart.
I'm fairly certain finding
a donor is no longer
this person's goal.
If we try interfering
with his plans directly,
he's sure to have fail-safes.
Now.
We'll need to stay in touch,
so, I'll open Whisper Mode.
We don't have much time.
Let's go!
Iori...
Please, take me with you!
No, I'm going to
Megin Fi alone...
But don't worry.
I promise you I will find Eri.
Iori!
Was that wise?
Our goals may be different,
but we're all looking for the
same ending to this debacle.
So I'll use every
pawn on the board.
When you come out of
the Chaos Gate, start
working your way down...
Follow the blood vessels
and you'll find the heart.
Got it.
Split everyone into six teams
and be ready to move out...!
Fire up the power reactor...!
I want this gun
loaded yesterday!
Move quickly, please!
No idle hands!
C'mon, hurry!
You are so not helping!
It's really damp
all of a sudden.
That means you're close.
Stay on your toes.
I will.
Okay...
Iori...?!
Damn it!
What's goin' on,
did somethin' happen...?
Wha--?
Hey!
Not yet.
No destroying it yet...
Sakuya's on her way.
So this was all your doing?
We've lost Whisper Mode...
Sakuya really was his goal!
Area keywords.
Uh...
Does Sakuya know the
truth about me, too?
Sakuya?!
She never once thought you were
anything but her friend...!
Now please, stop all this
and give Eri back!
Thank you.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Wait!
Hermit...!
What're you gonna do?!
Eri...!
What the--?!
Guess who?
Hermit, hi!
Eri is with the
bad guy below...
I can lead you there
if you want me to...
Brave Sakuya's gonna defeat
the evil villain trying
to destroy The World.
He's not a villain.
I found out that he's been
searching for a long time
for a genetic donor to
save a sick little boy...
So I know he can't
be a bad person.
You know, that boy
died a long time ago.
Turns out...
that I'm compatible.
So I...
I have to go tell him...!
Really...?
Asumi...!
Dammit...
That was awesome!
Eri?!
Asumi!
Get away from Hermit!
He's the one who did this!
Nice work...
You found the final boss.
Wait, what?
You heard her...
I'm behind all of this...
Now if you defeat me,
you'll have cleared this quest.
What're you saying, Hermit...?
"Defeat you," why?
I'm the one who's been turning
people into Lost Ones.
And I'm the dead
little boy, too...
Although, it was only recently
that I found out
about the dead part.
But see, I don't
remember how I got here...
I just woke up
as this character,
holding this black twig.
It lets me do pretty much...
whatever I imagine
in this world...
Kinda like...
a wizard or somethin'...
I thought it must've been God
who gave it to me as a blessing.
But I can't use it
to cure myself.
I told myself not to think about
what happened to the
people I poked with it...
Mostly because I was scared to,
but also because I didn't
see any other way.
Correct elevation...!
Target: The digital
bastille on Mag Mell!
Sakuya...
Erase me and end all this.
Dammit no!
There has got to be some other
way to fix this, Hermit!
I know it's a game
to everyone else,
but this place has
been my reality...
It hurts when I get cut...
and when I die.
But it never stops.
To keep on living when
I've got no future...
it's like I'm
trapped in a nightmare!
Let me end it.
On my mark...
and fire!
You made me happy...
You were the only one, Sakuya...
who ever called me "friend."
Can I...
ask one last, selfish favor?
D'you think...
you could gimme a hug?
Now I know why I was
drawn to you, Sakuya...
'Cause I've...
been looking for you forever!
M'sorry...
The incident during the
Christmas Territory War Event
was forgotten in
just a few weeks.
And The World went back to being
its same old lively self...
But as for Eri, Iori and me...
We couldn't quite
bring ourselves
to go back there for a while...
Not until the guild master
sent me that message.
Um, uh...
Hello?
Oh, Asumi!
Good, you're there!
I don't have much time--I'll
try to make this short.
It's about Hermit...
he's alive.
What?!
His father's connections
got the boy's body
preserved in cryonic
suspension...
which required him being
declared legally dead first.
That's how they connected him
to the digital bastille.
"Digital bastille"?
A system for
life-sentence criminals,
reducing them to mere
brains for imprisonment.
It uses a technology called
"soul digitization."
Yeah, um...
The digitized brains are used
as parts of a quantum computer,
while the brains
themselves are stored
in a cryopreservation
facility...
Seems the lab
preserving Hermit's player
supplied that technology.
Really?
So...
So rest easy.
Hermit does still have a body...
And he's no criminal.
There must be some puppet
master behind the scenes who
took advantage of him and made
him use the digital bastille...
I'm sure it's no coincidence
that you and Hermit met.
A "puppet master"...
not a god?
Call it what you like...
Come on, behave.
I can tell you the rest
in Aomori, okay...?
See ya then.
Ooh, Iori!
I haven't been to
your baths in forever!
Me first!
What are you, a child?
Yeah, so, I'm joining the donor
registry when I turn eighteen...
Then maybe...
I can see Hermit
after he's well.
Oh, yeah!
I think Hermit's
waiting for you, too...
It's obvious how much
he really liked you.
Jeez, Eri...
You talk about 'im like he's
your brother or somethin'!
Yeah, well--hey, I was
with him the longest.
And then all four of us
can play The World together!
What, after all we went through
you're not the
least bit worried?
Until soul digitization tech is
gone from The World completely,
it'll keep being used...
It'll just take on
a different form...
Which is why people like us
will always need to be
around to keep tabs on it.
That game is the world
my brother loved...
They won't have
their way with it.
Ew, don't throw
that in the bath.
I won't...
Night, Hermit...
I'll see you soon, right?