So how's Eri doing?
She still unconscious?
Mm-hm.
What do the doctors say?
They called it
photosensi-something.
I don't know...
They talked like they thought
it was from gaming too much.
So it should be
all right then...
People recover from
this photo-whatever?
But they say it usually
only takes a few hours.
Then it's not super-serious...
She'll be awake and back to
normal before you know it.
Not this.
This either...
It's just no use...
I need the list.
Without it, I can't
see their data.
Whatever else happened, I do
hope Sakuya didn't get PK'd.
Wonder what she's like
in the real world--
bet she's pretty cool...
Wish I could meet the real her.
Wait a minute.
I hope the real "her"
isn't actually a "he".
Lemme think...
Cat-boy fell from up here, and
then a black hole opened up...
We know that much.
Either something's at the
other end of that hole...
or our feline friend's
got himself a secret.
Guess I'll use process
of elimination.
No communications
devices in the hospital.
Please turn that off.
Sorry.
Thank you very much, doctor.
So what's the deal?
My hand's still a little numb,
but they told me
it'll heal soon enough...
They also said I needed
to stop gaming for a while.
Oh, okay...
Well, then...
Shall we?
Hey, she's gone.
Did they release her?
Sorry, 'scuse me...
Where's the girl who was
in this bed earlier?
Oh...
they transferred her to a
different hospital this morning.
I knew it.
What?
Look at this right here...
CC Corp.'s an investor.
See, there's this rumor
going around about players
who collapse in The World...
Apparently, back in real life
they get put in hospitals
that are quietly
controlled by CC Corp.
People are saying it might
be some sort of cover-up.
Cover-up?
Yeah...
concealing the
connection between The World
and these comas.
Think about it.
Didn't you say
before you passed out,
you touched Eri and your
real body got flung back?
Um, yeah...
Uh-huh...
And I bet you touched
her with this hand.
There's this freaky urban legend
I've heard about The World...
It's all about how people's
souls will get trapped inside
the game, and their characters
keep walking around
even though the players
themselves are unconscious.
Stop.
I don't wanna hear it.
You're freaking me out...
It's just identity theft.
Yeah, it's possible...
but I doubt it.
The things that have
been happening recently
are disturbingly synchronized
with in-game events.
And that random hospital
transfer--don't you think
it's strange that she was
moved out of the city
when the first place was newer?
There was no reason for it.
CC Corp.
must be beh--
Iori...
just stop!
If there's anything I can do
to help Eri, I want to...
But I don't understand all
this conspiracy theory stuff.
It scares me to think about.
An online game?
Yeah, everybody says
it's really cool!
Come on, you have
to play with me!
No way...
Sounds pretty dorky.
So not my thing.
What?!
Well, I'm here.
Oh!
Cool!
You picked
a Black Rose type, huh...?
I guess that
makes us partners!
And who's this guy?
Oh right, this is my
other partner, Tobias...!
We got to know each other
back when I first started
playing The World.
Nice to meet you.
Make sure you have
the right attributes...!
I'll send him to you
with a Knockback Move,
so make a skill attack!
Love to, but what
does that mean?
Sakuya, behind you!
Huh?
Asumi?
So...
what do you think?
What you said earlier...
Is Eri trapped in
The World somehow?
I don't know...
but I sincerely hope she isn't.
Because if she is...
then I have no idea
what we can do about it...
Not even the slightest clue.
You want a ride?
Nah, I feel bad always
making you drive me.
But I was wondering...
Would it be okay if I came over
after school's out tomorrow?
It's just all that stuff
you were telling me...
I can't bring myself
to believe it...
it's still so scary...
Anyway...
If there's anything I can do
to help, I want to.
I mean, it's up to us, isn't it?
We're the only ones
who know what happened
before she went into the coma.
Hey, there's my customer!
I brought that list,
as requested.
Pretty much the
same as last time.
Users with microchips
all documented...
Also...
I went ahead and added the users
who weren't around before.
Thought you'd dig that.
But password analysis
on two hundred thousand
people's data...?
That's all you.
Too boring for me, man.
Thank you.
What the heck are you
gonna use it for, anyway?
It's secret.
Hey...
be careful not to
get caught, yeah...?
I don't want you to
take me down with you.
Thanks for the warning.
This should do it
for the analysis.
I can forget about the one
I lost at this point...
It's not like it can
be traced back to me.
Guess I can go ahead and
add the ones who got PK'd.
Kind of figured we'd be doing
more detective type stuff
in here.
Precisely what we're
doing, dear Watson.
Hey, look at your right hand.
I don't get it.
What's happening?
My best guess is
it's got something to do
with the numbness.
We'll check it out later, okay?
Yeah.
All right...
This is where we
pick up the trail.
Jump in, Sakuya.
Here I go!
Cannonball!!
So much for that.
We can write it off
as a warp hole, but where
does that leave us...?
This Hermit...
I think he's involved somehow.
What's happening to me?!
What do think this is?
Some kinda scroll...
Do you know where you found it?
I have no idea.
What the heck?
It looks like...
people's personal information!
Iori, look at this!
No way!
What the hell is going on?
This is nuts.
Eri...
Masaya Asanuma...
0 5 9...
1 8 F D...
0 B C 2.
Got it.
Koichi Matsubara.
Phone number: 0 4 6 7 D 9 A...
B C 1 A, You got all that?
Uh-huh.
Next up we have Kana Sugimoto...
0 9 8 D A 1 2...
B D C C.
So...
Do you think all
these people are players
who've slipped into comas?
That's the question...
Time to start checking.
What're you gonna do?
Hit up my sources.
Jeez...
they're all hospitalized.
And what's more, CC Corp.
is an investor in
all these hospitals...
Gotta say even I didn't
expect somethin' this big...
Is this a good idea?
What d'you mean.
Just think...
We're getting ourselves involved
in something major here!
We should call the pol--
Number's blocked.
And they sure are persistent.
It's probably just one
of the families I talked to
calling back.
Land line?
What?
Ikuta residence.
Just a second, please...
Iori!
Phone!
That moron.
Thank you for holding.
May I help you?
Is this Iori Ikuta?
Well, that depends.
Who is this?
You just made
several phone calls.
And every number
belonged to a Lost One...
Eri Eto has only been
Lost for a week...
How did you
figure it out so quickly?
Tell me who you are...
And how do you know about Eri?
I'm conducting
an investigation.
I don't mean you any harm...
I'm going to send you
two tickets...
I want you and your
other friend to come to Tokyo.
I'll email details and
the exact location shortly.
What in the world have
we gotten ourselves into?
Who made this?
And what did they
plan to do with it?
Sakuya!
Oh, Hermit, hey!
You're okay, then!
I've been looking
all over the place for you.
Oh, really...?
Sorry.
Is there something wrong?
A Lost One?
Yeah...
It was my friend who got PK'd.
She was with us before...
You know, Mary?
I got a call from this
place called the NAB...
they said it's been
happening a lot lately.
Well, that's it for me.
I need some sleep.
Oh.
But...
you'll come again
tomorrow, right?
I'm sorry...
I've got somewhere to be.
Bye for now!
It's the only clue
we have so far!
What else can we do?
I'm just saying we need
to be a bit more careful.
We don't know who was on the
other end of that phone call.
It'll be okay if you
don't wanna come.
I can go by myself.
Don't be like that.
I never said I wasn't going!
Tokyo's huge...
Look at all these people.
It's this way.
Let's go.
Look, it's the U.N. University.
"NAB investigator"?
We'll see about that...
Yes?
Both of you log in, please.
Come to the far door.
Iori!
There are certain problems that
are endemic to The World...
What you see are players
who fell into comas
because of those problems.
If you know so much,
why do you need us?
Of course, the official position
is that current medical science
cannot prove a link between
what happens in the game
and the players'
subsequent comas.
Welcome to my sanctum.
Hey wait, you're--
I'm sorry about that
whole 'bounty' mix-up.
It's all right.
I'm sorry, t--
So you called us all the way
here just to show us that?
Come now, no need to be cross.
The cause of these comas
lies within the game.
And so too, does the means
to wake up the victims.
You'd better not be spinning
stories to get information
out of us.
It won't work.
I'm not lying...
Perhaps it will set your mind at
ease to know that I was party
to the 'incident'
five years ago.
The tragic events of
Twenty-Seventeen were caused
by a powerful consciousness.
And the Lost Ones could not
be revived until that threat
was eliminated.
But they did eventually
come back, then?
Yes...
with some exceptions,
they returned...
Now...
I'd like to know how the two of
you came upon your information
regarding the current Lost Ones.
That's easy.
Net Slum.
I'm being honest with you.
Why can't you show me
the same courtesy?
What's "honest" about
meeting in character...?
If you want us to be
straight with each other,
why don't you show us
who you really are?
I thought things would
be smoother this way,
but perhaps I was wrong...
Very well.
Take off your FMDs.
Pleasure to meet you.
As a matter of pride,
I'd like to clarify...
That character in no way
reflects my normal style...
Her appearance is
merely convenient for
my unrelated search
for a missing person.
Yeah, whatever.
Now will you answer
my question honestly?
You told us about five years
ago, but you still haven't said
anything about this incident.
If I do, will you
tell me what you know?
If we find your story
to be believable.
But that could present
a problem, couldn't it?
What if I tell you the truth and
you don't find it believable?
Well...
If it's the truth,
then we'll believe it.
Shut up!
She seemed sketchy on
the phone and in her email...
but we still came
here, didn't we?
Let's trust her.
CC Corp.
has had serious problems
ever since it first released
The World...
Those problems
have been exploited
in any number of ways...
In the end, however,
they are rooted in the ideals
of one misguided researcher.
He dreamt that he could free
humanity from the evil of racism
by turning everybody
into a Lost One.
That dream drove
his every action
and spiraled out of control...
Between the fire at CC Corp.
in Twenty-Fifteen and his
subsequent lapse into a coma,
the curtain closed
on the matter...
at least for the time being.
However, an organization
exists committed
to carrying on his research...
Their immediate objective is
to gain control
of all the Lost Ones.
They've already entered the
practical application stage
with people who never have
to come back to reality...
They use people
whose disappearances
won't cause problems.
Astounding.
This is literally
a record of his crimes...
Where'd you get this?
I'm not sure...
I pick stuff up without
looking at it all the time.
I see...
All right, well I'll be
taking charge of this for now.
If we can give the data a close
look, we may be able to identify
who made the list through
quirks in his programming...
For now, leave the
rest in our hands...
And both of you stay
far away from The World.
Smith'll facilitate
further communications.
Stop playing the game?
But our investigation--
For all we know, you nearly fell
into this criminal's clutches.
Restrain yourselves until
we know for certain
you aren't being targeted.
I feel like I've been
hit upside the head with
a blunt instrument...
It's unsettling to have
someone prove to you you're
a tiny fish in a big sea.
C'mon, it's not that bad.
So she has a lot of information.
You still know
plenty of stuff I don't.
Well, that sure
isn't saying much.
Just teasin'...
Thank you.
Well, I'll be damned, boy.
Do you see now?
I want to cut them out of
the system and set them free.
Dude, do you even
understand what this is?
Huh-uh.
Look right here.
Every single one of these babies
is fourteen billion
superposed qubits.
Smart money says
the brains' synapses
are bein' used for
qubit interactions...
Quantum computers are just
plain amazin', y'ask me.
Can you do it?
Easy as pie with
the ones on the ground.
They'll disconnect for sure...
The brains are parts now,
though, they may not make it...
Ah, don't worry boy.
I'll get 'em out
nice and clean for ya.
Hee-hee-hee!
This is gonna be good!
Your friend in the coma...
how is she doing?
No change, unfortunately.
I'm sorry...
We've gotten some results
I can share with you...
I'll do my best to explain.
This list has been
constructed as a database
of user haplotypes.
Okay.
What are those?
To put it in simple terms,
they're basically
genetic types...
From the research we've done,
it looks as if the owner of
the list was searching
The World for a donor
to help a particular patient.
Why look for this 'donor' in
The World instead of real life?
No doubt exploiting the game's
vulnerabilities was the
more convenient route...
Haplotype data is highly
sensitive private information,
and as such is safeguarded by
extremely complex firewalls.
But if you were to use
social security numbers--
Hold on a sec--the
government oversees
our real-world identities.
Whoever this person is,
how could he extract that
kind of data from the game?
Here.
Allow me to demonstrate.
It's my list!
We were able to determine the
list-maker's motive because
the patient's ID is
in the database, too.
He's an American citizen,
so it did take us some
time to track him down.
But you found him, right?
Yes.
The intended recipient
is a Toha--Tanagami...
He was in a hospital
in San Francisco
awaiting treatment
until Twenty-Fifteen.
You said "was".
So he's already been released
from the hospital, then?
No.
He passed away...
He's been dead seven years.
Someone's looking for donors
for a person who died?
That seems to be the case, yes.
But now we know the
reason behind all this.
Whoever made the list
is stealing data from
The World for Tanagami's sake.
Passed away?
Seven years ago?
He forcibly
extracts biological data
from the owners of these IDs...
As a result,
they become Lost Ones.
Sakuya, I need you
to tell me your password.
Huh?!
What the crap?
I'm almost done with it, dude.
All of this, and for nothing!
Seven years, just wasted!
Man, what's up with you?!
As long as a hacker has an
FMD and a modicum of skill...
Implant chip security's
just not that tough to crack.
That doesn't make sense!
There's nothing more private
than internal microchips!
What I've just shown you
proves that's not true.
What's this?
"Compatible"?
What's up?
Mistress!
Attention Players:
This field is about to be shut
down for server maintenance...
What's happening?
Again, this area
is shutting down...
Please log out.
They're eating people!
This is insane!
Mistress, from what I can tell,
the area's being hacked.
Can you take care of it?
I'll do what I can.
Eri!
What?
Come back!
Eri--!
That hurt!
It hurt?
Log out now...!
We're not in Mac Anu anymore!
It's not working!
Hey, what did you do to her?
It's a Data Drain...
but she's recovering
from it too quickly!
Damn it...
Get offline!
If they PK you,
you'll become a Lost One!
No, not yet!
Eri's coming with us!
How?
There's no way!
Sakuya!
I'm left with no choice.
Forgive me.
Eri!
Territory war...
loneliness...
dark clouds...
underground...
freeze...
rampage...
karma...
chaos...
Donor...
recipient...
despair...
rebirth...
denouement...
On the next episode of
.hack//Quantum.