HI, GUYS, IT'S TAI.
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
IT'S NICE TO SEE
KEN AND THE OTHERS
GETTING ALONG BETTER.
EVEN CODY WAS INVITED
TO HIS CHRISTMAS PARTY.
AND WHAT A GREAT PRESENT
THEY GAVE US OLDER KIDS
BY BRINGING
OUR DIGIMON BACK.
WE WENT
TO SEE MATT'S BAND PLAY,
BUT THESE DIGITAL MONSTERS
STOLE THE SHOW.
NO ONE COULD DIGIVOLVE
BECAUSE SOMEONE PUT UP
A CONTROL SPIRE.
KARI AND THE OTHERS
CRUSHED IT,
AND WE SENT ALL THOSE MONSTERS
BACK WHERE THEY BELONG.
KEN KNEW ARUKENIMON
WAS BEHIND THE CONTROL SPIRE,
AND NOW THAT SHE'S OPENED UP
ALL THE DIGIPORTS,
OTHER DIGIMON CAN COME AND GO
AS THEY PLEASE!
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Man: WE INTERRUPT THE "POWER
RANGERS ARBOR DAY SPECIAL"
FOR THIS SPECIAL
NEWS BULLETIN.
STRANGE BLACK TOWERS THAT BEGAN
APPEARING LAST NIGHT IN ODAIBA
HAVE NOW BEGUN SPRINGING UP
ALL AROUND THE WORLD.
THEY WERE FIRST THOUGHT
TO BE A MARKETING SCHEME
FOR A DOT-COM COMPANY.
WAIT A SECOND.
I'VE JUST BEEN HANDED SOMETHING.
OKAY,
WE'VE JUST BEEN INFORMED
THAT LARGE MONSTERS
HAVE NOW BEEN SPOTTED
IN THE AREAS
OF THESE TOWERS.
YOU'RE ADVISED TO LOCK
YOUR DOORS AND STAY INSIDE.
DIGIMON!
HERE IS A LIST OF AREAS
WHERE THE MONSTERS
HAVE BEEN SPOTTED --
THE HILLS NEAR ASO...
[ GROWLING ]
THE AREA ADJACENT
TO THE CLOCK TOWER IN SAPPORO...
NEXT TO OSAKA CASTLE...
THE AREA NEXT TO TAMACHI STATION
IN TOKYO...
DID HE SAY TAMACHI?
THE GRASSY KNOLL
IN DALLAS, TEXAS...
VENICE BEACH IN CALIFORNIA --
ALTHOUGH NO ONE'S NOTICED YET.
RIGHT, OKAY,
I GOT IT.
ALL OF US ARE GOING TO MEET
OVER AT IZZY'S HOUSE.
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR, DAVIS?
COME ON. LET'S GO!
I CAN'T.
RIGHT NOW I HAVE TO GO
TO TAMACHI.
YOU HAVE TO WHAT?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR THE NEWS?
THERE'S DIGIMON IN TAMACHI.
THAT'S WHERE KEN LIVES.
HE'S PROBABLY BEGGING
FOR MY HELP RIGHT NOW.
HOLD ON. TAMACHI ISN'T THE ONLY
PLACE IN TROUBLE, YOU KNOW.
PEOPLE ALL OVER THE WORLD
NEED OUR HELP.
WE CAN'T WORRY
ABOUT ONE INDIVIDUAL.
NOW LET'S GO TO IZZY'S HOUSE
AND COME UP WITH A PLAN.
HE'S NOT AN INDIVIDUAL,
HE'S ONE OF US!
BUT, DAVIS --
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
OKAY, THEN, I'LL TAKE CHARGE
OF EVERYTHING ON THIS END.
YOU GO ON TO TAMACHI
AND HELP OUT KEN.
RIGHT.
Man: REPORTS CONTINUE TO COME IN
FROM AROUND THE WORLD
OF THESE GIANT MONSTER ATTACKS.
OUR VIEWERS MIGHT REMEMBER
THAT A SIMILAR EVENT
TOOK PLACE FOUR YEARS AGO.
ARMED FORCES AROUND THE GLOBE
ARE TRYING TO ATTACK,
USING THE INFORMATION
THEY GATHERED
IN THOSE ORIGINAL BATTLES.
HOWEVER, EVERY TIME THEY GET
CLOSE TO ONE OF THE MONSTERS,
THEY SUFFER
FROM EXTREME EQUIPMENT FAILURE.
IN OTHER WORDS,
NOTHING WORKS.
ALSO, THE WORLD'S MILITARY
COMMUNITY IS CLAIMING
THAT ANY DATA STORED IN
THEIR COMPUTERS FROM THAT TIME
HAVE MYSTERIOUSLY VANISHED
FROM THEIR HARD DRIVES
WITHOUT A TRACE.
STAY TUNED TO THIS NEWS STATION
FOR ROUND-THE-CLOCK COVERAGE
OF THIS UNBELIEVABLE
CATASTROPHE,
BUT FIRST,
HERE'S JOHNNY WITH SPORTS.
MY FRIEND, YOU LOOK
1,000 YEARS YOUNGER.
THANK YOU, AZULANMON.
AMAZING WHAT
A FEW DIGIVITAMINS CAN DO.
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU --
A DIGICORE.
I THINK YOU KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
REMEMBER, ITS POWERS ARE NOT
TO BE TAKEN LIGHTLY.
I'LL REMEMBER.
THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
YOU'LL NEED IT
IF BOTH WORLDS
ARE TO SURVIVE.
HEY, LOOK, I'M GETTING E-MAILS
FROM KIDS ALL OVER THE WORLD.
WHOA,
TALK ABOUT DéJà VU.
AND THEY'RE NOT JUST KIDS.
THEY'RE DIGIDESTINED KIDS.
HOW CAN THAT BE?
THERE'S OVER 200 E-MAILS
ALREADY.
ARE YOU TELLING ME
WE'RE NOT
THE ONLY DIGIDESTINED GOING
AROUND SAVING THE WORLD?
TO BE HONEST,
I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
HOW MANY DIGIDESTINED EXIST,
BUT I'M GUESSING ANY KID WHO'S
EVER SEEN A DIGIMON QUALIFIES.
LIKE WILLIS IN AMERICA, AS WELL
AS MIMI'S FRIEND MICHAEL,
OR ANY KID THAT SAW OMNIMON
LIKE YOLEI DID
DURING OUR BATTLE
OVER THE INTERNET.
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THERE COULD BE THOUSANDS
OF DIGIDESTINED
AROUND THE WORLD.
HEY, MAYBE WE SHOULD FORM
SOME SORT OF UNION.
WELL, LET'S ANSWER
ALL THOSE E-MAILS
SO WE CAN FIND OUT
JUST WHO HAS A DIGIVICE
AND WHO DOESN'T.
OKAY, TAI, YOU WRITE BACK
KIDS IN EUROPE.
MATT, YOU TAKE
NORTH AND SOUTH AMERICA.
SORA, YOU'VE GOT AFRICA,
AND, JOE, WHY DON'T YOU ORDER US
SOME SANDWICHES?
I'VE ALWAYS DREAMED
OF AN ENTIRE WORLDWIDE ARMY
OF DIGIDESTINED,
AND I'M THE LEADER.
All: OH, BROTHER!
Man: JOHNNY, THAT TRADE
SHOULD REALLY HELP THE TEAM.
NOW BACK
TO THE EMERGENCY.
[ SCREAMING ]
GRRAAH!
I'M TRICERAMON!
GET MY POINT?
WELL, YOU WILL IF I USE
MY TRI-HORN ATTACK ON YOU,
AND DON'T BOTHER
HITTING BACK.
MY SHELL IS THE HARDEST
OF ANY DIGIMON ALIVE!
[ SCREAMING ]
WORMMON,
YOU'D BETTER DIGIVOLVE.
[ GRUNTING ]
I CAN'T DO IT.
I'M ALL DIGIVOLVED OUT.
THAT CAN ONLY MEAN
ONE THING.
Arukenimon's voice:
SEE, MUMMYMON,
I TOLD YOU HE WAS SMART.
WARMER, WARMER...
BURNING UP!
ARE YOU LOOKING
FOR LITTLE OLD ME?
YOUR FRIENDS AREN'T HERE
TO SAVE YOU THIS TIME.
TOO BAD, BECAUSE TRICERAMON
LOOKS HUNGRY.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
THUNDER BLAST!
[ GASPS ]
Ken: DAVIS!
KEN!
WE'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT DIGIMON.
DIGIVOLVE NOW,
VEEMON!
WORMMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
VEEMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
X-VEEMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
WORMMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
STINGMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
SPIKING STRIKE!
VEE-LASER!
GOOD LITTLE DIGISAUR.
DON'T JUST STOMP ON THOSE KIDS,
USE YOUR HORN!
HE WON'T LISTEN TO YOU,
FOOL.
HE'S NOT UNDER THE POWER
OF THE CONTROL SPIRES.
HE'S A REAL DIGIMON
WHO JUST HAPPENS
TO BE IN THE WRONG PLACE
AT THE RIGHT TIME.
WHERE ARE THE REST
OF THOSE KIDS,
AND WHY DID ONLY ONE OF THEM
COME TO HELP
THEIR MISERABLE FRIEND?
WELL, THEY'RE PROBABLY
ON THE INTERNET,
TRYING TO SELL OFF
THEIR TRADING CARD COLLECTIONS
BECAUSE THE WORLD
IS COMING TO AN END,
AND THERE'S NOTHING
THEY CAN DO ABOUT IT.
LET'S DNA DIGIVOLVE!
YOU BETCHA!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
X-VEEMON!
STINGMON!
Both: DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
PAILDRAMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
PAILDRAMON, GET HIM
INTO THE DIGIPORT!
PAILDRAMON, NO!
ARUKENIMON, I KNOW
YOU HAVEN'T TAKEN
MY AFFECTION FOR YOU
SERIOUSLY YET.
LET ME PROVE MY LOVE FOR YOU
BY DESTROYING PAILDRAMON.
DON'T GO AWAY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
OH, NO! MUMMYMON!
OH, GREAT!
NOT NOW!
SNAKE BANDAGE!
PAILDRAMON, WATCH OUT!
Izzy: THESE ARE THE LOCATIONS
WHERE THE DIGIPORTS HAVE OPENED
AND THE DIGIMON
HAVE APPEARED.
THERE'S MORE FLASHING LIGHTS
HERE THAN A CHRISTMAS TREE.
WE HAVE TO FIND SOME WAY
TO SEND THEM ALL BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
THROUGH THOSE DIGIPORTS.
ONLY ONE PROBLEM
WITH THAT THEORY --
ALL THE DIGIPORTS
HAVE CLOSED.
WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO TO EACH ONE
OF THOSE LOCATIONS
AND USE THE D-3s
TO OPEN UP NEW GATES.
ISN'T YOLEI'S UNCLE
A TRAVEL AGENT?
WELL, YEAH, BUT HE'S NOT
A MIRACLE WORKER.
MAYBE WE CAN ALL TRAVEL
THROUGH THE DIGITAL WORLD.
ONLY ONE PORT AT A TIME
IN EACH AREA
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD
CAN BE OPENED.
IT COULD TAKE US MONTHS
TO TRAVEL ALL OVER THE WORLD.
WE DON'T HAVE
MONTHS!
THE WAY THE CONTROL SPIRES
POP UP, IT'S MORE LIKE DAYS!
IF WE DON'T FIND A WAY
TO DESTROY THEM,
WE WON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT TRAVEL PLANS
BECAUSE THERE WILL BE
NO PLACE TO TRAVEL TO.
WE'VE GOT ONE CHANCE.
THINGS MIGHT GET
A LITTLE CRAZY.
EVERYBODY, STAND BACK.
Upamon: I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
[ ALL GASP ]
AAH! A GHOST!
NO, I'M NOT A GHOST.
WOULD A GHOST
LOOK THIS GOOD TO YOU?
ALL RIGHT! IT WORKED!
WE'RE REAL GLAD YOU CAME.
THANKS A LOT, GENNAI.
I'VE ALWAYS TOLD YOU,
IF YOU EVER NEED ME,
JUST CALL.
YOU MEAN YOU'RE GENNAI?
I THOUGHT, UH...
LAST TIME WE SAW YOU,
YOU WERE AN OLD MAN!
MY HAT'S OFF
TO YOUR PLASTIC SURGEON!
UH...FORGIVE ME, BUT YOU'RE
THE MOST INCREDIBLE HUNK
OF AN INCREDIBLY OLD MAN
I'VE EVER SEEN!
I'M YOLEI.
GENNAI, OUR WORLD'S
BEING ATTACKED.
WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE.
I KNOW, IZZY.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
WOW, THAT'S COOL.
WHAT IS IT?
LISTEN CLOSE. THIS WAS GIVEN
TO ME BY AZULANMON.
IT'S ONE
OF HIS 12 DIGICORES.
THE POWER OF THIS SPHERE
IS UNLIKE ANYTHING
YOU'VE SEEN BEFORE,
SO IF ANYONE'S SQUEAMISH,
I SUGGEST YOU BACK OUT NOW.
READY?
HOLD UP YOUR DIGIVICES.
I FEEL KIND OF FUZZY.
YOU ARE FUZZY.
HEY, I FEEL IT, TOO.
UPAMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
ARMADILLOMON!
BOROMON,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
HAWKMON!
LOOK, THEY DIGIVOLVED...
IN OUR WORLD!
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
HMM.
DAVIS, KEN, WATCH OUT!
HUH?
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PAILDRAMON,
MEGA DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
IMPERIALDRAMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WHOA!
SO, GUYS, BE HONEST.
HOW DO WE LOOK?
WELL...
WELL, UH...
THAT USED TO BE...
PAILDRAMON?
[ GRUNTING ]
YES, BUT I HAVE DIGIVOLVED
TO THE HIGHEST LEVEL --
MY MEGA FORM --
IMPERIALDRAMON!
I AM STRONGER
THAN ANY OTHER DIGIMON.
MY MEGA CRUSHER ATTACK
IS VIRTUALLY UNSTOPPABLE!
ONE OF THE STRANGE MONSTERS
HAD A STRANGE LIGHT HIT HIM
IN A STRANGE WAY,
WHICH CHANGED HIM
INTO ANOTHER STRANGE MONSTER.
WHO IS THAT?
THAT IS
IMPERIALDRAMON.
THE POWER OF AZULANMON'S LIGHT
IS STRONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
PAILDRAMON USED IT
TO DIGIVOLVE TO HIS MEGA FORM.
GENNAI, IS THAT
THE SAME LIGHT THAT HIT US?
YES, THAT'S RIGHT,
GATOMON.
THAT LIGHT
IS ONE AND THE SAME,
WHICH MEANS YOU SHOULD NOW
BE ABLE TO DIGIVOLVE
TO ULTIMATE.
I CAN LET THE CAT
OUT OF THE BAG?
HOW COOL.
[ GROWLING ]
OH, NO,
HE DIGIVOLVED TO MEGA!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
THIS ISN'T MY DAY!
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
MORE BANDAGES THAN THAT!
AAH!
KEN! NOW!
GOT IT! DAVIS?
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
WE GOT HIM!
OKAY, NOW WE HAVE TO DESTROY
THE OTHER CONTROL SPIRES!
HOW? WE CAN'T TRAVEL
THAT FAR WITHOUT --
AAH!
WHOA!
Imperialdramon: I KNOW
WHERE THE CONTROL SPIRES ARE.
HANG ON!
POSITRON LASER!
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT,
THAT'S RATHER IMPRESSIVE.
WELL, WHILE YOU'RE
STANDING THERE
DROOLING OVER
YOUR NEW HERO,
I AM GOING TO DEVISE
A NEW PLAN OF ACTION.
THAT'S IMPERIALDRAMON
ALONG WITH DAVIS AND KEN!
YES, BUT I'M AFRAID
THIS IS TOO LARGE OF A TASK
FOR THEM TO HANDLE ALONE.
YOU EACH HAVE JOBS TO DO.
WE MUST WORK TOGETHER,
OR ALL WILL BE LOST.
HUH?
Ken: IT'S UP TO YOU NOW,
IMPERIALDRAMON.
Davis: COOL! WHO'S NEXT?
I HAVE A QUESTION.
IF IT'S REALLY BEEN FOUR YEARS,
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING
ALL THIS TIME?
I'VE BEEN CLEANING UP
SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
YOU WERE VERY YOUNG
AT THE TIME, CODY,
BUT DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN
THE DIGITAL WORLD APPEARED
IN THE SKY
ABOVE THE EARTH?
YES,
I REMEMBER THAT.
WELL, UNFORTUNATELY,
PEOPLE ALL OVER THE WORLD
SAW IT, TOO,
AND THEY ALSO SAW THE FINAL
BATTLE WITH APOCYLAMON.
SINCE THEN, SCIENTISTS
AND MILITARY AROUND THE WORLD
HAVE BEEN TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO GET
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
CAN YOU IMAGINE
IF THEY WERE TO SUCCEED?
WHY, PEOPLE WOULD WANT
TO TRAVEL THERE
FOR A VACATION LIKE IT WAS
THE BAHAMAS OR SOMETHING.
SOON, THERE WOULD BE DIGIMON
SINGING CALYPSO MUSIC
AND SERVING
FROUFROU DRINKS.
SO WE'VE SECRETLY
BEGUN CHANGING
ALL THE DATA IN THE COMPUTERS
HERE ON EARTH
TO KEEP THE DIGITAL WORLD
HIDDEN.
GRRAAH!
NEXT UP -- KYUSHU!
YOU SAID "WE."
DOES THAT MEAN
THERE ARE OTHERS OUT THERE
LIKE YOU, GENNAI?
THAT'S RIGHT,
ONLY NOT AS GOOD-LOOKING.
MY ALLIES ARE POSITIONED
AROUND THE WORLD
WORKING WITH OTHER
DIGIDESTINED LIKE YOU
TO STOP THIS DISASTER.
AAH!
ALL RIGHT! THAT TAKES CARE
OF ALL THE DIGIMON
WHO HAVE APPEARED HERE
IN JAPAN!
OKAY, LET'S HEAD BACK
TO ODAIBA!
ALL RIGHT, GENNAI,
WE ALL UNDERSTAND
WE HAVE WORK TO DO.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS POINT US
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
WE HAVE PICKED SIX OTHER
STRATEGIC LOCATIONS
AROUND THE WORLD
WHERE THE DIGIMON
HAVE RECENTLY APPEARED.
THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED
ARE MEETING MY ALLIES
IN THOSE SPOTS.
THOSE COMMAND POSTS
ARE IN NEW YORK, HONG KONG,
MOSCOW, MEXICO CITY,
SYDNEY, AND PARIS.
HEY, LOOK, EVERYBODY!
KEN AND DAVIS HAVE RETURNED.
Gennai: NOW, LISTEN,
THE DIGIPORTS WON'T OPEN
WITHOUT A D-3,
SO IMPERIALDRAMON
WILL TAKE EACH OF YOU
TO ONE
OF THE SIX LOCATIONS.
I WANT YOU TO JOIN FORCES
WITH THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED
AND LEAD THEM INTO BATTLE.
YOU MUSTN'T STOP
UNTIL ALL THE DIGIMON
HAVE BEEN DEFEATED.
ANY QUESTIONS?
YEAH, ONE --
FLYING ON IMPERIALDRAMON
WAS COOL AND EVERYTHING,
BUT DO YOU THINK
WE CAN GET A MOVIE AND SOME
OF THOSE HEADPHONE THINGS?
IMPERIALDRAMON TRAVELS FASTER
THAN THE BLINK OF AN EYE,
SO YOU WON'T HAVE TIME
FOR A MOVIE. TRUST ME.
WELL, MY FRIENDS,
GOOD LUCK ON YOUR JOURNEYS.
WE SHALL MEET AGAIN...
SOON.
WAIT!
DON'T LEAVE US YET!
HE'S GONE!
I'M SURE HE'S GOT MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO
THAN HANG AROUND HERE
WITH US.
ALL RIGHT, WE KNOW WHAT TO DO.
IS EVERYONE READY?
YOU BET!
Woman: IZZY, WAIT!
Izzy: MOM,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
LISTEN, MOM, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT US.
ALTHOUGH I MAY BE GONE
A WHILE,
I PROMISE TO COME BACK
AS SOON AS I CAN.
UH, WHAT'S THAT?
WHEN I SAW
ALL THE REPORTS ON TV,
I KNEW
YOU'D BE LEAVING,
SO I MADE YOU SOME RICE
BALLS FOR YOUR TRIP.
THANKS, MOM,
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
I LOVE YOU.
MATT, T.K.!
TAKE CARE!
OH, TERRIFIC, THERE'S
TOO MUCH STATIC IN THE AREA.
I CAN'T EVEN GET
A PICTURE!
DON'T WORRY. IT'S PROBABLY
FOR THE BEST.
[ ALL GASPING ]
BEFORE YOU FACE THE BIGGEST TEST
OF YOUR LIVES,
THERE'S IMPORTANT INFORMATION
YOU NEED TO KNOW!
YOU'RE FREE TO MOVE
ABOUT MY CABIN.
HOWEVER, WHEN THE "FASTEN
SEATBELT" LIGHT COMES ON,
PLEASE RETURN TO YOUR SEATS
AND BUCKLE UP.
SHOULD WE LOSE PRESSURE
DURING THE FLIGHT, DON'T PANIC.
IT'S PROBABLY
JUST SOMETHING I ATE.
WELL, THERE GO
ALL OUR PLANS
FOR DESTROYING
THE WORLD.
I THINK MY BIORHYTHMS
ARE REALLY OFF TODAY.
I'M GOING HOME
AND GOING STRAIGHT TO BED.
[ CELLULAR PHONE RINGS ]
RIGHT.
OKAY, GOT IT.
YOUR PLANS FOR A NAP
WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
WE'VE GOT
OUR NEW ORDERS.
YEAH, WHAT?
WHILE THEY'RE OUT
GLOBETROTTING,
JAPAN IS LEFT DEFENSELESS!
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
NOW LET'S GET GOING.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO WASTE.
RIGHT.
Announcer: WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
GET BACK IN TIME
TO STOP ARUKENIMON
AND MUMMYMON?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."