We found tons and tons of
control spires
so we decided not to leave
again until we destroy the
Digimon Emperor's headquarters.
We told our parents we
were going camping and
the older kids went for
real to cover for us.
The Digimon Emperor's
base had vanished and
Yolei went ballistic.
She and Hawkmon were
attacked by Dokugumon and
Hawkmon was badly hurt.
Yolie felt so bad, she
told us to go on and look
for the base without her.
Hawkmon woke up, and they
saw the Digimon Emperor's
base floating in the sky.
If he can make his
base fly, who knows
what else he can do?!
♪ Di - Di - Di ♪
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪Di - Di - Di ♪
♪ Di - Di - Di ♪
♪ Digimon, the digital monsters,
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Change into digital champions
to save the digital world ♪
♪ Digimon, the digital monsters,
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Digivolve into champions ♪
♪Digivolve into ultimate ♪
♪ Digimon, the digital monsters,
Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Digimon, the digital monsters
Digimon ♪
(snoring)
Does Davis always
snore like that?
Every night.
How do you sleep?
I don't.
Where are those
guys going?
I still think we
should have told the
others before we left.
It may be none of my
beeswax, but why didn't you
ask Davis to come with us?
I didn't want to leave Kari
and Yolei alone anymore.
Don't worry,
he'll understand.
I'm just glad I'm not going
to be the one to tell him.
The e-mail says they've figured
out which way the Digimon
Emperor is heading.
Let's see.
What do you mean they
left without me?
How come nobody wants
to go anywhere with me?
Well, Davis, it could
be your snoring.
Is it finished yet, Master?
Not quite. I still have a
few minor details.
Should he have
four arms or six?
Decisions, decisions.
(slurp)
We're getting an
update from Kari.
Any of you guys know
how to catch a fish?
(sighs)
I wish I had a T.V. dinner.
Alright. All I have to
do, is take the bus, to
the campsite, and Matt.
Wait! Don't go!
I want to get on!
Should we tell Davis
we're leaving?
Nah, he'll understand.
Why's everyone leaving?
Is it my snoring?
We've been flying for hours
and haven't seen a thing.
I'll check with Cody and
see if he's seen anything.
What did TK say?
They haven't spotted
anything from up above.
Well, we haven't
seen much of anything
either, except seaweed.
Maybe we should turn back.
Huh?
What is that thing?
Let's dig a little further.
This thing is enormous.
It makes Texas look
like Rhode Island!
It has to be the
Digimon Emperor's base!
I'll let TK know
that we found it.
Huh?
It's from Cody.
They found the base
and are going to try
and sneak in through
an underwater cave.
That sounds kind
of dangerous.
Maybe they should wait.
TK, look!
Huh?
A whirlpool.
Oh, no. They'll get
sucked right into it!
Hmm, looks like
it's finally here.
What is that,
Master, a new way to
hypnotize your slaves?
No, you fool.
You might call it a
gateway to the source of
the powers of darkness.
But for simplicity's
sake, let's just call
it the Dark Pool.
I think it's caused by an
evil digimon, and if I
can tap into it's power,
then I'll have everything
I need to complete my
very own Digimon.
Please, Master,
don't do it!
What are you
talking about, of
course I'll do it.
But it feels like
evil itself is coming
from that Dark Pool.
You can't feel
it, because you're
not a Digimon.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not going to stop my
master plan because of a
silly feeling of yours.
But on the evil scale of
one to ten, that dark
pool is really evil.
(laughs)
Fine.
Then you stay
away from it.
In the meantime, I've
got things to do.
Please don't ignore me.
Oh, I'm sorry how's this?
A huge whirlpool?
And Cody and Submarimon
are inside the base?
We've got to warn them!
Try to contact
them with the D3!
Don't you think I've
tried that already?
Something seems to be
blocking the transmission.
We can't just hover here.
We've got to do something!
Tentomon's right.
We're running out of time!
Yeah.
Are you guys feeling okay?
Well, I think I might
be getting a bug, but,
other than that, I'm fine.
I am feeling a
little strange.
How about you, TK?
I'm not really sure.
I... I feel kinda weird.
I'm tired.
Don't they have an
escalator in this place?
Whoa!
My thoughts exactly.
This has to be
the engine room.
I say we destroy this
place once and for all.
We will but, let's take
a look around first.
Alright, if you say so.
Hey, do you think it's
kinda cold in here?
Not especially.
That's weird Cause I just
can't seem to warm up.
The chill of evil
is in the air.
Don't be so dramatic.
You know what
this place needs...
More window space.
There!
Master I know you hardly
ever listen to me.
Okay, you never
listen to me.
But, please, just this
once, do what I ask.
Don't do it!
Hmm. I'm sorry
I wasn't listening,
did you say something?
Look, it's on the move.
And heading for
the whirlpool.
Cody.
We're moving!
Armadillomon, look!
This place is like a prison.
It must be where the
Digimon Emperor keeps all
of his captured slaves.
I guess you guys didn't
have a very good lawyer.
So what are we going
to do about them?
This is more important
than the engine room.
You'd better armor
digivolve and break
the bars open.
Now that's a good idea.
Digiarmor... Huh?
What is that thing?
My thoughts precisely.
(evil laugh)
Now, into the dark whirlpool.
(more evil laughter)
Ah, it's not that funny.
Thanks for the lift, Grandpa.
I can't believe they
left without taking me.
So, you're going camping?
That's nice.
We used to do lots of
camping, didn't we dear?
Yeah, until that time I
used poison ivy instead
of toilet paper.
Huh?
(sighs)
Davis, what are you doing?
I'm thinking about how
we can make a canoe
out of this tree.
Great!
How are we gonna do it?
First, we gotta
push this tree down.
A little too hard.
Beats a canoe.
Ah!
Smell that salt air.
Hey Davis, how come
we're on land and
I'm getting seasick?
That's the biggest mobile
home I've ever seen.
It must be impossible
to find parking.
Come on guys, we've got to
find the cave that Cody
and Armadillomon
used to get inside.
Hurry up, they
might be in trouble.
(scary howling)
This place feels... evil.
Don't pay any
attention to them.
What are those things?
They're just trying
to scare you.
They live in
the dark whirlpool
and feed off fear.
(scary howling)
Don't look at it!
Can I sit up here
with you guys?
Look... this has
to be the cave!
Hmm?
Master?
Are you all right?
Never been better.
Initiate the attack!
(scream)
What's going on?
They're gone!
How'd that happen?
Sector A, report.
Sector B, come in.
Sector C, where
is everybody?
They were never very
good at spelling.
(growl)
Where are you going?
If you want something done
right, do it yourself.
This one's stuck.
Oops.
Cody!
Hi guys, I'm glad you're
here, we were just
setting these captive
digimon free.
Why didn't you say so,
that's my specialty!
Super Shocker!
I can just tell, there's
something out there.
Master, please come back.
You don't know what's out there.
Quiet!
Devimon!
(laugh)
Impossible!
I'll take what I need
from this digimon,
then my digimon
will be completed!
Are you sure?
Huh?
Do you really believe
you can control the
powers of darkness?
Alright, who are you?
I am here to warn you:
beware the darkness.
(evil laughs)
Beware the darkness?
Ha, I'm the
digimon emperor.
I rule this world and
some voice comes out of
nowhere and tells me to
beware the darkness?
Who does he think
he's kidding?
(big laugh)
Of all the digimon that
are out there, why did
it have to be Devimon?
I'll never forget our
battle four years ago.
Angemon faced
Devimon one on one.
It was our last chance to defeat
Devimon, once and for all.
Be careful!
(Laughs)
I'll get him, relax.
Angemon knew what
he had to do.
Ohhh! Ahhh!
The only way to completely
destroy Devimon's evil powers
was for Angemon to
sacrifice himself.
Come here pretty boy!
I begged him
not to do it.
But, we both knew
there was no choice.
I always felt that
it was my fault.
That maybe I could've
done something.
But, it was too late.
I was too young back then
to know how to handle it.
Too young to understand.
Well, that was then
and this is now!
Huh?
Are you okay, TK?
Cody, I've got some
unfinished business
to take care of.
Time to get to work!
TK, wait a minute!
TK!
Where's he off to?
Uh...
Maybe we should
follow him?
Don't worry, Patamon will
take care of TK.
We need to keep working
to free these digimon!
You're right.
How could he not
know who I am?
I've told everybody.
Huh?
Well, what do you know?
I have visitors.
It's those kids.
I don't have time to
deal with those annoying
brats right now.
You sure have
changed, Master.
You used to love trying to
destroy the digidestined.
It was your favorite
thing to do,
next to putting coal in
children's Christmas stockings.
Bah, Humbug.
Now, for the final touch!
There!
My masterpiece is
finally completed!
Nothing can stop me now!
(snores)
She sure can snore!
No louder than you!
Gee, Davis, the rest
of the guys must
be way ahead of us!
Yeah, we're just gonna
have to go faster.
I still can't believe
Kari did this to me.
Yolei, do you think Davis
is really mad at us?
Naw, he's a
pretty good sport.
Hey, look at that!
It's heading right for us!
Alright, everyone,
get ready!
If I had known I was
having this many guests,
I would've catered!
Oh, I can still give
them a party favor!
Go get them!
(low growl)
Do you see what I see?
(roar)
What is that thing?
(laughs)
Chimeramon is
my ultimate creation!
I combined the most
powerful parts of other
digimon to form this
unstoppable
fighting creature!
His Heat Viper attack
will melt my enemies
into oblivion!
(roar)
I've never heard of a
digimon like that before
and I get all the news
from the underground!
Listen Cody, while those
guys do battle with him,
we can free the prisoners!
Let's go!
(roar)
Tempest Wing!
That's why I picked
Kabuterimon's head,
they don't come
any more hard headed!
Cat's eye beam!
And he's fast with Angemon
and Airdramon's wings!
Play time's over.
Now, it's my turn!
(roar)
Throw in Garurumon's legs, as
well as Monochromon's tail.
I added Kuwagamon's,
Skull Greymon's and
Devimon's arms.
His body is Greymon's and
I topped him off with
Metal Greymon's hair.
He's perfect!
(laughs)
Where's my VCR?
Oohhh, I wish I was taping this.
Take a good look
at him, Wormmon.
Now that's what a partner
should look like.
Not a scrawny
runt like you!
(sigh)
Okay, that's the last one.
It's time we got
out of here too.
We can't leave without TK.
He'll be fine.
We've got to get these
digimon to safety.
Let's go!
TK, can't you do this later?
We've got to get out
of here while we can.
Don't be so stubborn!
I don't remember sending
you an invitation.
I must admit, you
have a lot of nerve.
Sneaking into the base of
the most powerful being
in the digital world!
(Laughing)
What's so funny?
Let me ask you
something, Ichijouji.
Don't you think it's
time you gave up on
this little charade?
It's getting old.
You say you're the most
powerful being in the
digital world, and yet,
you have no idea about
the powers that are here.
You're a pretender.
You're like that story,
the emperor's new clothes.
(gasp)
You're nobody!
Not like me!
You will bow
down before me!
Sorry, The floor's
kinda dirty.
You will listen to me!
(gasp)
When you can't think of
anything to say,
do you always
resort to fighting?
I guess.
That's your problem.
You don't know when to
talk and when to fight.
Now's a good time to talk.
On the other hand, it's
also a good time to fight!
Nefertimon, Halsemon!
You guys be careful, okay?
Heat Viper!
Hey!
Tempest Wing!
Rosetta Stone!
(roar)
They had no effect!
Oh no!
Sticky Net!
Boom Bubble!
Wanna fight?
Actually I'd prefer
a staring contest.
Halsemon!
Let's get out of here!
What's that thing?
(roar)
Didn't I tell you?
I have a new pet.
Chimeramon!
My secret weapon that's
not a secret anymore.
Don't worry if you
didn't get a good look.
You'll see him up close
and personal real soon!
(roar)
TK?
Digiarmor Energize!
♪ Digimon, Digimon,
Digimon, the digital monster ♪
Patamon Armor
Digivolve to...!
♪ Digimon, the digital monsters,
Digimon are the champions ♪
Armor, digivolve.
♪ Digimon, the digital monsters,
Digimon are the champions ♪
Pegasusmon, flying hope!
Digimon!
Hey Ken, remind me
where we left off
the next time I'm
pummeling you into oblivion.
Master?
I guess I'm not as
cool as I think I am.
Off day? Hmm?
Time for me to
regroup and come back
stronger than ever.
Equus Beam!
Thanks Pegasusmon!
It was just a
little horse play!
Chimeramon's
stopped moving.
Let's take this opportunity
to get out of here!
♪ Together ♪
Here's your hat back, TK.
I didn't want anyone
to step on it.
That's okay, Cody.
I have six others just like it.
One for each day of the week.
I'm ready to fight and all
the action's over with!
I wish we'd gotten
here sooner.
The other digimon
can fly, why can't I?
Come on...
You've got your own fighting
skills like that head of yours
is as hard as mine!
Right!
Anyway, let's hear
it for TS who really
let Ken have it!
(cheer)
Um, that's TK.
Are we at the right camp site?
I guess they told
you the wrong place.
Why wouldn't Matt give me
the right information?
Could it be he doesn't
want me around?
She's just as
sharp as Davis.
What is the next step in
the battle for control
over the Digiworld?
Tune in to the next
Digimon: Digital Monsters!