T.K.: WE WAITED FOR OIKAWA
TO SHOW UP
AT HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE.
HE TOLD US HE WAS GOING
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT WE FIGURED
THE SEALED GATE WOULD FAIL
AND WE COULD CAPTURE HIM.
WE WERE WRONG. WE FOLLOWED
OIKAWA TO A STRANGE DIMENSION
WHERE WE FOUND OUT
MYOTISMON
HAD BEEN CONTROLLING HIM
FOR YEARS.
MYOTISMON DIGIVOLVED
TO MALOMYOTISMON
AND DESTROYED
ARUKENIMON AND MUMMYMON.
AFTER THAT, ALL WE COULD
THINK ABOUT WAS
WHAT HE COULD DO
TO OUR DIGIMON FRIENDS.
EVERYONE BUT DAVIS, THAT IS.
HE AND X-VEEMON HAVE GONE AFTER
MALOMYOTISMON.
I DON'T THINK I'VE BEEN
GIVING DAVIS ENOUGH CREDIT.
HE'S THE BRAVEST PERSON
I KNOW.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ ROARS ]
HA HA HA HA!
AAH!
HE'S TOO POWERFUL, DAVIS.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE HE TURNS X-VEEMON
INTO A HANDBAG.
NO! I'LL NEVER RETREAT!
NOT AS LONG AS THERE'S
A FIGHTING CHANCE.
I'VE NEVER QUIT BEFORE,
AND I'M NOT GOING TO START NOW.
AS LONG AS X-VEEMON
IS WILLING TO FIGHT,
I'M BACKING HIM.
[ GROWLING ]
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP,
DAVIS!
IT'S WORKING.
IT'S WORKING!
V-LASER!
SO YOU WANT TO PLAY
HARDBALL, DO YOU?
ALL RIGHT!
GO, X-VEEMON!
MAKE HIM SHUT
THAT UGLY MOUTH OF HIS!
V-LASER!
MENTAL ILLUSION!
[ GROANING ]
HEY, MOM.
SORRY I'M LATE. HUH?
HELLO THERE, SON.
JUST IN TIME FOR DINNER.
MOM MADE YOUR FAVORITE
GOULASH.
OH...HA HA HA!
WOW,
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE THE WHOLE FAMILY'S
BEEN TOGETHER.
[ GROANING ]
WOW! I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
THERE MUST BE TWO DOZEN
DIFFERENT DESSERTS HERE.
ARE THEY ALL FOR ME?
[ LAUGHS ]
THEY'RE ALL FOR ME?
YAY, YAY, YAY!
ALL FOR ME! YAY!
[ GROANING ]
DAD, THIS IS
THE DIGITAL WORLD
I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
IT CAN BE
PRETTY STRANGE AT FIRST,
BUT YOU GET USED TO IT.
HMM.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO SOME OF THE DIGIMON.
THEY MAY LOOK SMALL,
BUT THEY'RE PRETTY POWERFUL.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
SOME OF THE CRAZY STUFF
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH.
I THINK YOU'D BE PROUD.
[ GASPING ]
IT'S SO NICE.
HEY, ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
KARI?
HUH?
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD TELL ME
WHEN I CAN EXPECT NYAROMON
TO DIGIVOLVE TO SALAMON.
DO YOU TAKE
GOOD CARE OF HER?
YEAH, OF COURSE I DO.
DON'T WORRY.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE GIVING HER
LOTS OF LOVE,
SHE'LL DIGIVOLVE
SOON ENOUGH.
OH. HA HA.
HA HA HA!
ALL FOR ME!
[ Thinking ] I HOPE
YOU'RE PROUD OF ME, DAD.
SO I HEARD A JOKE TODAY.
A DUCK WALKS
INTO A PHARMACY
AND ASKS THE CLERK
FOR SOME LIP BALM.
THE PHARMACIST SAYS,
"CASH OR CHARGE?"
AND THE DUCK SAYS,
"JUST PUT IT ON MY BILL."
HA HA HA HA.
T.K.?
HEY! PATAMON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I CAME TO GET YOU.
WE NEED YOU.
WHAT? BUT I'M NOT
FINISHED EATING DINNER.
NONE OF THIS IS REAL.
IT'S AN ILLUSION.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, PATAMON?
LOOK, MY FAMILY'S
FINALLY ALL TOGETHER.
HUH?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
DON'T GO.
PATAMON, DO SOMETHING.
I WANT THEM TO STAY.
IT'S NOT REAL.
[ Gasps ] WAIT A SECOND.
THEY WEREN'T HERE AT ALL.
MALOMYOTISMON,
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY!
THERE YOU ARE, DUDE.
DAVIS?
SO, ARE YOU READY
TO HELP ME?
MM-HMM.
MMM. THIS IS SO GOOD.
I KNOW I'M GOING TO GET
A STOMACHACHE,
AND I DON'T EVEN CARE.
YOLEI, MY DEAR,
IS THIS REALLY
WHAT YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED?
HUH? WELL, OF COURSE.
DESSERT IS MY FAVORITE MEAL.
DO YOU LIKE NOT HAVING YOUR
BROTHERS AND SISTERS AROUND?
YEAH, IT MEANS
MORE FOR ME.
[ SIGHS ]
ACTUALLY, I KIND OF MISS
THEM RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE ALWAYS SURROUNDED
BY YOUR BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
AND YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU GET PASSED OVER,
SO YOU'VE WONDERED
WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
IF THEY WEREN'T AROUND.
AM I RIGHT?
YOU'RE RIGHT. I GUESS
I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED
WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
TO BE AN ONLY CHILD.
BUT I LOVE MY BROTHERS
AND SISTERS,
AND I LOVE
HAVING THEM IN MY LIFE.
MM-HMM!
THANK YOU, HAWKMON.
I GUESS I WAS BEING
A REALLY BIG OINKER
BACK THERE.
SOMETIMES IT TAKES
SOMEONE TO SHOW YOU THINGS
A LITTLE MORE CLEARLY.
YOU'RE THE GREATEST
FRIEND EVER.
YOU'RE MAKING
MY FEATHERS BLUSH.
HEY, GUYS, WE COULD
REALLY USE YOUR HELP.
MM-HMM!
AND THAT'S
HOW WE DEFEATED DAEMON.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
MMM.
CODY!
HUH?
ARMADILLOMON. I'VE BEEN
LOOKING ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I WANT YOU TO MEET
MY DAD.
CODY, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S YOUR FATHER.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HE'S RIGHT HERE.
THIS ISN'T REAL.
ARMADILLOMON, I THINK I KNOW
MY OWN FATHER WHEN I SEE HIM.
HE'S JUST BEING FUNNY, DAD.
HMM...
AHH!
AAH! NO!
WAIT, DAD. DON'T GO!
Armadillomon:
CODY, THIS IS AN ILLUSION.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S GONE.
HE LEFT AGAIN.
I NEVER GOT TO SHARE
THE DIGITAL WORLD
WITH MY DAD.
I WON'T MAKE
THAT MISTAKE AGAIN.
I'M GOING TO SHARE
THIS WORLD WITH MY MOM.
I HOPE SHE CAN HANDLE IT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
ABOUT THAT, ARMADILLOMON?
I SAY IT SOUNDS
LIKE A WINNER.
LET'S GO.
HUH?
FLAMEDRAMON!
COME ON, LET'S GO.
EVERYONE'S WAITING
FOR US, CODY.
YEAH.
ISN'T THIS JUST
WONDERFUL, GATOMON?
HUMANS AND DIGIMON
PLAYING TOGETHER
WITHOUT SOME LUNATIC
TRYING TO DESTROY IT ALL.
YEAH, BUT --
WHAT IS IT?
I HATE
TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT THIS ISN'T THE WAY
THINGS REALLY ARE.
HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HAVE YOU BEEN
INTO THE CATNIP AGAIN?
IT'S ALL
A BIG ILLUSION.
YOU MEAN
NONE OF THIS IS REAL?
WHAT NERVE.
GATOMON, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE AM I?
HUH?
RAIDRAMON!
COME ON, KARI,
WE NEED YOU.
MALOMYOTISMON
CAST A SPELL
OVER ALL OF THE DIGIDESTINED
TO DISTRACT YOU.
TRUST ME,
I KNOW HIS TRICKS.
SO THEN WE WOULDN'T
PUT UP A FIGHT.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN LAZY.
THAT'S WHY HE NEEDED ME.
BUT THOSE DAYS ARE OVER.
I'M WITH YOU NOW, KARI.
LET'S GO.
[ GROANING ]
I THINK I GOT SAND
IN MY BRAIN.
HUH?
WAIT, THERE'S SOMETHING
UP AHEAD.
I HOPE
IT'S A WATER FOUNTAIN.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
THERE'S A PERSON UP THERE.
WAIT. IT'S -- IT'S --
[ Gasps ]
IT'S THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
Ken: IT'S ME!
[ PANTING ]
[ Thinking ] THERE'S NO WAY.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
[ PANTING ]
[ Gasps ]
WAIT. WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE'VE COME TO GET
SOME PAYBACK.
YEAH, FOR ALL THE PAIN
AND SUFFERING
YOU CAUSED DIGIMON
THROUGHOUT THE DIGITAL WORLD.
NOW IT'S OUR TURN.
MAYBE YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
HOW HELPLESS WE FELT
WHEN YOU WERE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
TAKE THIS!
AAH!
[ GROANING ]
HUH?
WAIT A SEC.
SAM, I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD.
I'VE COME BACK TO INVITE YOU
TO STAY WITH ME HERE,
WHERE YOU NO LONGER
HAVE TO SUFFER
FOR THE ERRORS
OF YOUR PAST.
YOUR PUNISHMENT IS OVER.
I'M YOUR BROTHER. TRUST ME.
I CAN'T GET THESE VISIONS
OUT OF MY HEAD.
IF I STAY,
WILL YOU HELP ME?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'VE MISSED YOU, SAM.
Wormmon: KEN,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WORMMON,
WHAT HAPPENED TO SAM?
HE WAS NEVER REALLY HERE.
BUT HE PROMISED
TO HELP ME.
YOU CAN'T CHANGE
YOUR PAST, KEN.
YOU CAN ONLY CHANGE
YOUR FUTURE.
MY BROTHER
WAS AN ILLUSION?
MALOMYOTISMON.
THAT'S IT.
I'M TIRED OF BEATING MYSELF UP
FOR WHAT HAPPENED IN THE PAST.
I'M NOT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR ANYMORE.
I'VE PAID FOR MY MISTAKES.
I KNOW THAT,
AND SO DO ALL OF MY FRIENDS.
HOW DARE HE USE
MY BROTHER AGAINST ME?
I'M NOT A TOOL
FOR DARKNESS ANYMORE,
AND MALOMYOTISMON
CAN'T CHANGE THAT.
YOU SAID IT.
WE GOT YOUR BACK, KEN.
DAVIS, T.K.!
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS, DUDE.
YOU CAN COUNT ON US
NO MATTER HOW BAD IT GETS.
DAVIS IS RIGHT, KEN.
WE'RE A TEAM.
YOLEI!
WHEN ONE OF US FALLS DOWN,
ANOTHER ONE OF US
PICKS THEM RIGHT UP.
THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
IT'S A TWO-WAY STREET,
KEN.
KARI!
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS,
AND WE NEED YOU
AS MUCH AS YOU
NEED US.
WITHOUT YOUR EXPERIENCE,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE WE'D BE.
SHE'S RIGHT, KEN.
CODY!
BUT WE CAN'T TELL YOU.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE IT
FOR YOURSELF.
I DO BELIEVE IT.
WE'VE WAITED A LONG TIME
TO HEAR THAT.
HEY, HANDSOME, IT LOOKS LIKE
YOUR LITTLE MAGIC TRICK
DIDN'T WORK. WE'RE BACK.
[ GROWLS ]
TAKE HIM, GUYS.
[ ROARING ]
FIRE ROCKET!
THUNDER BLAST!
V-LASER!
[ GROWLS ]
CHECK IT OUT, DAVIS.
THEY REALLY HURT HIM.
BUT HOW DID X-VEEMON SPLIT
INTO HIS THREE DIGIVOLUTIONS?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE,
NOT EVEN FOR THIS CRAZY PLACE.
IT WAS REALLY WEIRD.
I WAS WISHING
THAT X-VEEMON COULD GET
STRONGER, AND IT JUST HAPPENED.
MALOMYOTISMON WAS MAKING
MY BLOOD BOIL,
SO I WISHED X-VEEMON
WAS STRONG ENOUGH TO STOP HIM.
THEN THERE WAS THREE OF HIM.
HOW IS
THAT POSSIBLE?
SOMEHOW IN THIS WEIRD DIMENSION
EMOTIONS BECOME REALITY.
DAVIS MUST HAVE
TAPPED INTO SOMETHING.
ARE YOU READY, PATAMON?
YOU BET!
I DON'T WANT THE POWERS
OF DARKNESS
TO HURT ANY OF MY FRIENDS.
PATAMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
PATAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
PEGASUSMON, GALLOPING HOPE!
MAGNAANGEMON.
ANGEMON!
WHAT'S THIS?
HAND OF FATE!
STAR SHOWER!
HAWKMON, ARE YOU READY
FOR SOME ACTION?
INDUBITABLY.
WE ARE STRONG. WE ARE STRONG.
WE ARE STRONG!
HAWKMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
HAWKMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
HAWKMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
SHURIMON, SAMURAI OF SINCERITY.
AQUILAMON!
HALSEMON, THE WINGS OF LOVE.
[ GROWLS ]
GRAND HORN!
TEMPEST WING!
DOUBLE STARS!
READY TO JOIN THE PARTY?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
I WANT MALOMYOTISMON
TO BE STOPPED
BEFORE HE CAN HURT
ANY MORE DIGIMON.
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
ARMADILLOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
SUBMARIMON,
RELIABLE GUARDIAN OF THE SEAS.
ANKYLOMON!
DIGMON, THE DRILL OF KNOWLEDGE!
[ GROWLS ]
GOLD RUSH!
OXYGEN TORPEDO.
TAIL HAMMER!
IT'S OUR TURN.
IT'LL BE MY PLEASURE.
THE FUTURE OF BOTH WORLDS
DEPENDS ON US.
MALOMYOTISMON MUST BE STOPPED.
GATOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GATOMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
NEFERTIMON,
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT.
ANGEWOMON.
[ GROWLS ]
ROSETTA STONE!
CELESTIAL ARROW!
AAH!
ARE YOU READY, PAL?
I'M READY.
LET'S DO IT.
WORMMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
STINGMON!
SPIKING STRIKE!
SO, YOU'VE TAPPED INTO
THIS DIMENSION'S POWER.
I UNDERESTIMATED
YOU INSECTS.
BUT DID YOU THINK
YOUR RIDICULOUS DIGIRATS
COULD HURT ME?
[ GRUNTING ]
WELL, YOU WERE WRONG.
NOW IT'S MY TURN, KIDDIES.
CRIMSON MIST!
ANKYLOMON!
ANGEMON!
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
SHAKKOUMON!
T.K.: GO GET HIM,
WHAT'S THIS?
AQUILAMON!
GATOMON!
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
SILPHYMON!
STATIC FORCE!
GO, STINGMON!
X-VEEMON!
STINGMON!
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
PAILDRAMON!
HUH?
DESPERADO BLASTER!
AAH!
WE'VE GOT HIM ON THE ROPES.
LET'S FINISH THIS GUY OFF!
PAILDRAMON,
MEGA-DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
IMPERIALDRAMON!
[ GROWLS ]
IT'S OVER, MALOMYOTISMON.
IMPERIALDRAMON,
MODE CHANGE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FIGHTER MODE!
[ GROWLS ]
Davis: LOOK AROUND YOU.
YOU'RE OUTMATCHED.
EVERY DIGIMON HERE
WANTS A PIECE OF YOU,
AND I DOUBT YOU CAN
FIGHT THEM ALL.
I SUGGEST YOU SURRENDER.
I SEE IT,
BUT I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS TOTALLY DEFIES EVERY
SINGLE LAW OF SCIENCE.
I KNOW, BUT SOMEHOW
DAVIS REFUSING TO GIVE UP
EVEN WHEN MALOMYOTISMON
HAD US BEAT
CREATED SOME KIND OF FORCE
THAT MADE ALL THIS
CRAZY STUFF POSSIBLE.
I HAVE TO ADMIT IT --
DAVIS REALLY RULES.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
HIS BULLHEADEDNESS
WOULD STAND BETWEEN ME
AND NEVER-NEVERLAND.
T.K.: TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I MUST ADMIT, I'M IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR TENACITY.
WAIT TILL YOU SEE
MY BULLHEADEDNESS.
I'M CURIOUS TO KNOW
WHY MY MIND ILLUSION
WAS INEFFECTIVE
AGAINST YOU.
HOW CAN IT BE THAT YOU
HAVE NO INSECURITIES
OR UNHAPPINESS FOR IT
TO FEED OFF OF?
WHAT DO I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT?
I'VE GOT MY FRIENDS,
MY FAMILY, THE DIGIMON.
BESIDES SOME GUY WITH
A LETTER OPENER ON HIS FACE
TRYING TO KILL ME,
I'M HAPPY TO SAY
I DON'T HAVE ANY PROBLEMS.
IMPOSSIBLE. THERE'S NOT
A SINGLE CHILD IN THE WORLD
THAT DOESN'T HAVE SOMETHING
THEY'RE WORRIED ABOUT.
WELL, YOU JUST MET ONE.
CONGRATULATIONS, BIG AND UGLY.
I GUESS YOU SHOULD GO BACK
TO YOUR MAGIC ACT.
NOW, IF WE'RE THROUGH
CHITCHATTING,
I'D LIKE TO GET BACK
TO THE PART
WHERE WE PUT YOU AWAY.
I'M SICK OF MONSTERS LIKE YOU
ALWAYS TRYING TO TAKE OVER
THE WORLD.
IT'S OVER.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO LET YOU
HURT ANY MORE PEOPLE.
HUH?
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS,
LET HIM HAVE IT!
POSITRON LASER!
AAH!
WHAT A SHOT.
All: YEAH!
Both: HUH?
Davis: HE WENT
RIGHT THROUGH THE WALL!
I THOUGHT HE'D GO
THROUGH TWO WALLS
WITH THAT SHOT.
WAIT.
WHERE ARE WE, GUYS?
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ALL
BACK IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
ALL THE OTHER
DIGIMON DISAPPEARED.
IT'S BACK TO NORMAL,
IF YOU CALL THIS NORMAL.
HEY, WHERE'S MALOMYOTISMON?
[ MANIACAL LAUGHTER ]
CHILDREN,
WERE YOU LOOKING FOR ME?
HA HA HA HA!
THANK YOU FOR SENDING ME
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
WHERE I AM MOST POWERFUL.
YOU FOOLISH CHILDREN
PLAYED RIGHT INTO MY HANDS.
NO WAY!
HA HA HA HA!
LOOK, HE'S GETTING BIGGER.
THE DARKNESS -- I CAN FEEL IT.
IT'S COMING.
HA HA HA HA!
COME ON, GUYS.
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
WATCH AND LEARN.
HA HA HA HA!
OOPS. I THINK
I BROKE YOUR FRIENDS.
IT'S A SHAME
THEY WON'T BE CONSCIOUS
TO WITNESS
MY MOST TRIUMPHANT MOMENT.
NOW, BEHOLD MY POWER!
HE RIPPED OPEN A HOLE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD!
IT LOOKS LIKE IT LEADS
RIGHT TO THE REAL WORLD.
HIS POWER IS STARTING
TO SPREAD
OVER THE ENTIRE PLANET.
I KNEW IT.
IT'S BEEN HIS PLAN
ALL ALONG
TO GET BOTH WORLDS.
IT'S REMARKABLE
HOW SLOW YOU ARE, KEN.
YOU DIDN'T THINK
I COULD BE SATISFIED
RULING ONLY THE DIGITAL WORLD?
WITH BOTH REALMS SHROUDED
IN THE POWER OF MY DARKNESS,
I WILL RULE BOTH HUMAN
AND DIGIMON ALIKE,
AND THERE WILL BE
NO ONE TO STOP ME.
NOT WHILE I'M HERE!
WHEN WE FOUGHT HIM
THREE YEARS AGO,
HE SAID
THE EXACT SAME THINGS.
IT LOOKS LIKE HE HASN'T
CHANGED AT ALL SINCE THEN.
WELL, HE'S A LOT MORE
POWERFUL, THAT'S FOR SURE,
AND HE'S A LOT CRAZIER
THAN THE LAST TIME
WE ALL FOUGHT HIM.
Davis: COME ON, GUYS,
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
TO TAKE THIS GUY OUT.
THERE ARE BILLIONS OF HUMANS
AND DIGIMON COUNTING ON US.
Kari: BUT, DAVIS,
WHAT CAN WE DO?
THE DARKNESS IS SPREADING
SO QUICKLY.
IT'LL TAKE A MIRACLE
TO STOP HIM NOW.
[ Thinking ] KARI'S RIGHT.
BUT WHERE CAN I FIND A MIRACLE?
WILL MALOMYOTISMON
ENVELOPE BOTH WORLDS
IN HIS SHROUD OF DARKNESS?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."