Kari: AFTER RESCUING
THE GADZUMON FROM PRISON,
GATOMON SAW THIS STRANGE
CONTROL SPIRE.
MEANWHILE, THE EMPEROR
AND HIS VEGIMON SLAVES
CAPTURED GABUMON
IN A VILLAGE OF GAZIMON.
RED VEGIMON THREW GABUMON
INTO THE RIVER,
BUT HE WAS ABLE TO CALL MATT
AND THE REST OF US FOR HELP.
WE RESCUED THE GAZIMON
BY PRETENDING TO BE PRISONERS,
BUT THE VEGIMON
FOUND US AGAIN.
WHEN RED VEGIMON
CRACKED THE CONTROL SPIRE,
GABUMON WAS ABLE
TO DIGEVOLVE TO GARURUMON.
THAT SPIRE WAS THE KEY
TO THE EMPEROR'S POWER,
AND OUR MISSION
IS TO DESTROY THE REST.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ GRUNTS AND GROANS ]
[ GROWLS ]
WORD IS IT'S COLD.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
OHH!
AAH!
GET UP!
HEY, QUIT IT!
THEY'RE ALL TIRED
AND NEED REST.
MAYBE SOMEBODY SHOULD
USE THIS WHIP ON YOU!
NUMBER ONE,
DON'T EVER TALK TO ME
WITHOUT CALLING ME "SIR."
NUMBER TWO,
DON'T EVER TALK TO ME!
WHOEVER AMONG YOU
CAN DEFEAT THIS CREATURE
WILL RECEIVE
A SPECIAL PRIZE PACKAGE.
SO WHO IS UP
FOR THE CHALLENGE?
[ GROWLING ]
[ GOMAMON MOANS ]
Joe: I KNOW ALL ABOUT GIZAMON.
THEY'RE AMPHIBIAN DIGIMON
WITH WEBBED FEET.
THEIR FINS CUT
THROUGH WATER LIKE KNIVES.
THEY WON'T ATTACK ME.
AAH!
Emperor: THAT WAS
WAY TOO EASY.
THEY'VE DEFEATED HIM.
TELL THEM WHAT THEY'VE WON.
RIGHT.
All: AAH!
HERE IS YOUR REWARD --
YOU ALL HAVE THE HONOR
OF BEING MY SLAVES.
NOW GET BACK TO WORK
BUILDING THE PRISON!
MOVE IT, WORMON! I WANT YOU
TO MAKE ME A HOT CHOCOLATE.
WHAT ABOUT GOMAMON?
LET HIM FREEZE!
[ MOANS ]
[ Thinking ] I'VE JUST
GOT TO CLIMB
UP THIS LITTLE HILL.
[ GRUNTS AND GROANS ]
[ Thinking ] OKAY,
MAYBE IT'S NOT
SUCH A LITTLE HILL
AFTER ALL.
HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
JOE!
[ BEEPING ]
GOMAMON!
SO, GUYS, ARE YOU READY
FOR THAT ANATOMY TEST TODAY?
YEAH. I SPENT THE NIGHT
LOOKING IN THE MIRROR.
I JUST REMEMBERED I FORGOT
TO REMEMBER SOMETHING.
I GOTTA GO!
HEY, CODY!
OH, HI, DAVIS.
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S UP? ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HOME. I'VE GOT KENDO PRACTICE
THIS AFTERNOON.
WHAT? PRACTICE LATER.
THE DIGIWORLD'S IN DANGER.
SORRY, BUT MY GRANDFATHER
IS THE TEACHER,
AND HE WOULD BE DISAPPOINTED
IF I MISSED A LESSON.
SEE YOU.
YEAH, BUT --
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
KARI, GREAT! I'M GOING
TO THE COMPUTER ROOM.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME WITH ME?
SURE. LET'S GO.
YOU AND I TOGETHER
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD?
FINALLY! IT'LL BE LIKE
MY DREAM COME TRUE!
EXCUSE ME?
I SAID I'M STUDYING FRENCH.
PARLEZ-VOUS?
[ WHIMPERS ]
I JUST CAN'T WIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE JUST GOT A DISTRESS CALL
FROM ONE OF THE DIGIMON.
WHO?
I'M NOT REALLY SURE YET.
I'VE GOT IT.
THE SIGNAL IS COMING
FROM ONE OF THE BLACK AREAS
CONTROLLED BY THE EMPEROR.
IT'S A LOT FURTHER
THAN ANY AREA WE'VE BEEN TO.
Kari: THIS SHOULD ADD
TO OUR FREQUENT-FLYER MILES.
ACCORDING TO THIS MAP,
THE EMPEROR'S AREA
IS GETTING A LOT BIGGER.
IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE HE
CONTROLS THE DIGITAL WORLD!
THEN EVERY SINGLE DIGIMON
IS IN DANGER.
ALL RIGHT. I'VE HAD
ENOUGH OF THIS CLOWN.
LET'S ALL HEAD
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD!
BUT WE HAVE TO WAIT
FOR CODY.
HE'S NOT COMING.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
HE SAYS
HE HAS KENDO PRACTICE.
ONE QUESTION -- WHAT'S KENDO?
AAH! AAH!
WHAT DID YOU HIT ME FOR?
YOU WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT KENDO IS.
[ PANTING ]
[ GASPS ]
HYAH!
LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, CODY?
YOU DON'T SEEM
TO BE CONCENTRATING ENOUGH.
I'M SORRY, GRANDFATHER.
YOU HAVEN'T LOST INTEREST
IN THE MARTIAL ARTS, HAVE YOU?
OR GRANDPA?
OF COURSE NOT!
I CAN READ FACES.
YOUR EXPRESSION TELLS ME
THAT SOMETHING
IS TROUBLING YOU.
YOUR FATHER ACTED THE SAME
WHEN HE WAS A BOY.
I HAVE BEEN TO MANY LANDS
AND MET MANY PEOPLE,
AND IN ALL MY TRAVELS,
I HAVE FOUND ONLY ONE THING
I CAN COUNT ON --
PRUNE JUICE!
YEP. TAKE TWO BIG GLASSES.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
HA HA HA!
HMM! YOU WANT SOME?
NO, THANKS.
MY PROBLEM IS
EVEN TOO BIG FOR PRUNE JUICE.
HMM?
THERE ARE OTHERS
COUNTING ON ME TO DO SOMETHING,
AND I'M AFRAID
I MIGHT LET THEM DOWN.
I ONCE TOLD YOUR FATHER,
PEOPLE WILL RELY ON YOU
ONLY TO THE EXTENT
YOU RELY ON YOURSELF.
TRY YOUR HARDEST,
AND YOU WON'T LET ANYONE DOWN.
RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO GO, GRANDPA.
THANKS FOR THE ADVICE.
SEE YOU.
NO PROBLEM IS TOO BIG
FOR PRUNE JUICE!
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
OH, BOY! I KNEW
CODY WOULD SHOW UP!
IT'S NOT CODY, OKAY?
NOW EVERYBODY HIDE!
All: AAH!
All: HUH?
IT'S JOE!
HI, GUYS.
[ WHIMPERS ]
WOW. IT'S STRANGE
SEEING THE DIGIMON
HERE IN THE REAL WORLD.
THIS IS JOE,
OUR OLD FRIEND.
OH, THE DOCTOR.
THAT'S REALLY COOL.
WOULD YOU MIND TAKING
A LOOK AT MY TONSILS?
THIS IS DAVIS AND YOLI.
JOE'S NOT A DOCTOR YET.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
WE GOT A DISTRESS CALL
FROM THE DIGIWORLD.
I KNOW.
IT'S FROM GOMAMON.
YOUR DIGIVICE
WAS TRIGGERED TOO?
CANDY!
HEY! THESE ARE SUPPLIES
FOR AN EMERGENCY.
DO YOU PLAN ON COMING
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD WITH US?
WE COULD USE YOUR HELP.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT GOMAMON.
THESE ARE THE DIGIVICES
OF THE NEW DIGIDESTINED.
THEY'RE THE ONLY THINGS
THAT CAN OPEN THE GATE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD!
IZZY GAVE ME
A HEADS-UP ABOUT THEM.
HE ALSO TOLD ME
ABOUT THIS JERK THE EMPEROR.
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S OPEN THE GATE!
Davis: RIGHT!
WHAT ABOUT ME?
CODY, YOU MADE IT!
YOU MADE IT! YOU MADE IT!
FORGIVE HIM.
HE'S HYPERACTIVE.
Davis: HEY, EVERYBODY,
THE GATE'S OPEN!
ALL RIGHT! COME ON!
LET'S GO!
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ OHH, OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ OHH, OH ♪
[ Shivering ]
GREAT! I HATE THE COLD.
KARI, ARE YOU OKAY?
MM-HMM.
I'M SORRY, BUT WE WEREN'T
PROPERLY INTRODUCED
BEFORE WE TOOK OUR TRIP.
MY NAME IS --
I'M FREEZING MY GOGGLES OFF,
AND YOU'RE INTRODUCING
YOURSELF? LET'S GET GOING.
HERE. YOU CAN USE
ONE OF THESE.
THEY'RE HAND WARMERS.
KARI?
THANKS A LOT.
BOY, LEAVE IT TO YOU,
GOOD OLD RELIABLE JOE!
I WATCH ALL THOSE
SURVIVAL SHOWS ON TV.
IT WON'T OPEN! AAH!
JOE, LOOK!
HUH? WHOA! GOMAMON!
All: HUH?
GOMAMON, SPEAK TO ME!
JOE.
WHAT DAY OF THE WEEK IS IT?
IT'S SATURDAY?
IT'S THURSDAY, BUT YOU
NEVER DID KNOW THE DAYS.
I HEARD FROM TENTOMON
THAT WE COULD USE THAT TV
TO CONTACT YOU
IF WE WERE IN TROUBLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO WIPE OUT
MY FIRST AID KIT.
I ALWAYS GET MISTY
AT HAPPY REUNIONS.
I ACTUALLY THINK
I'M GOING TO CRY.
DON'T. YOUR TEARS
WILL TURN TO ICICLES.
YOU REALLY
LOOK TERRIBLE, GOMAMON,
BUT I MEAN THAT
IN A NICE WAY.
I PICKED A FIGHT
WITH THE WRONG GUY,
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
HE'S BUILT ANOTHER
CONTROL SPIRE HERE, TOO!
WHAT'S THAT?
Kari: IT'S THE DIGIMON
EMPEROR'S SECRET WEAPON.
HE HUNTS DOWN DIGIMON
AND PUTS THESE
DARK RINGS AROUND THEM,
TURNING THEM
INTO HIS SLAVES.
THE CONTROL SPIRES
SUPPLY THE POWER.
Kari: AND NO ONE
CAN DIGEVOLVE.
Davis: I'M GOING
TO RIP IT DOWN!
Kari: WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO CROSS THIS ICE
TO GET CLOSE ENOUGH
TO DESTROY IT.
NOW I KNOW WHAT MATT MEANS
WHEN HE SAYS
I'M WALKING ON THIN ICE.
DID YOU BRING ANY SKATES?
SORRY, I'M ALL OUT.
HEY, JOE, DO YOU
HAVE ANY ROPE?
YEAH.
CLAW CHOP.
BIG BUZZ SAW.
VEE HEAD BUTT.
WHEW!
WELL, THAT'S DONE.
WHAT A GREAT SLED!
NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS GO FOR A RIDE.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
WE'RE PULLING.
COME ON, GUYS.
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU.
OKAY!
NOW MUSH!
[ SHOUTING AND LAUGHTER ]
SO THEY'RE HERE?
MM-HMM.
WHAT A WAY TO TRAVEL!
UH-OH.
WE'VE GOT VISITORS.
OH, LOOK! SNOWMEN!
HOW CUTE.
Tai: NO, THEY'RE FRIGIMON,
BUT WHAT'S THAT
AROUND THEIR LEGS?
All: HUH?
ATTACK!
Emperor: FREEZE THEM,
FRIGIMON,
WITH YOUR SUB-ZERO
ICE PUNCH!
IT'S AMAZING HOW
THESE DOCILE CREATURES
CAN BE TURNED
INTO SUCH ABOMINABLE SNOWMEN.
[ CRIES AND SHOUTING ]
THAT'S COLD.
FORGET ABOUT THE FRIGIMON.
THEY'RE NOT VERY FAST.
WE CAN OUTRUN THEM.
OUR MISSION IS TO DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE,
SO IT'S BETTER TO KEEP GOING
THAN TO WASTE TIME FIGHTING.
BUT THEY'RE ATTACKING US!
JOE'S RIGHT. RUN PAST THEM.
WE MADE IT THROUGH!
AIM FOR THAT HILL!
THEY MISSED US BY A MILE!
All: HUH?
Davis: IT'S AN AVALANCHE!
All: AAH!
OHH!
AAH!
CODY!
Gomamon: I'LL SAVE HIM!
[ CODY SHIVERING ]
WARMING UP YET?
DRINK THIS HERBAL TEA.
IT'S 10% HERBAL
AND 90% TEA.
THANKS A LOT, JOE.
BOY, THAT JOE
REALLY COMES PREPARED.
THAT'S NOTHING.
WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE HIM
DURING HAY FEVER SEASON.
WE'LL HAVE TO LEAVE
CODY HERE.
Joe: T.K.'s RIGHT.
I'LL STAY AND TAKE CARE OF CODY.
THANKS, JOE.
I'M GOING, TOO.
MY GRANDFATHER TOLD ME
IF I RELY ON MYSELF,
I WON'T LET ANY OF YOU DOWN.
Kari: YOU'RE NOT
LETTING US DOWN.
YOU'LL NEED
TO CONSERVE YOUR STRENGTH.
WE'VE GOT A LONG FIGHT AHEAD,
AND WE'RE GOING TO NEED YOU.
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL WAIT HERE.
DON'T BE GONE LONG.
WE'LL BE BACK
QUICKER THAN YOU CAN SAY
"DIGIMON EMPEROR."
ARE YOU OKAY?
A LITTLE TIRED.
ME TOO.
I COULD USE A NAP.
I VOTE WE TAKE
THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO GET SOME SHUTEYE.
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
I SHOULD BE OUT THERE
HELPING THE OTHERS.
I USED TO FEEL
THAT WAY TOO,
BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS NAUSEA,
AND THEN I BEGAN
TO REALIZE SOMETHING.
ALL OF US
ARE HERE FOR A REASON.
THERE'S A BIG PICTURE
THAT WE CAN'T SEE YET,
AND I DON'T MEAN
A WIDESCREEN TV.
US STAYING BEHIND
IS FOR A REASON.
BUT WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
COME ON! LET'S GO!
All: AAH!
HA HA HA!
Emperor: MEET
MY NEWEST SLAVE SHELLMON.
HIS AQUA-BLASTER ATTACK
SHOOTS WATER SO HARD
IT CAN DEMOLISH SOLID ROCK!
IT APPEARS I'VE DISCOVERED
YOUR SECRET LITTLE HIDEOUT.
GOMAMON, NOW I KNOW
THE REASON
WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO STAY BEHIND --
SO THE OTHERS COULD
HAVE TIME
TO DESTROY THE SPIRE.
KEEP HIM BUSY WITH THAT
GREAT GOMAMON CHARM OF YOURS.
GOTCHA.
WHY DID ONE SHELLMON TAKE
THE OTHER SHELLMON'S LUNCH?
BECAUSE IT WAS SHELLFISH!
I GUESS YOU HEARD
THAT ONE ALREADY.
[ Thinking ] THAT'S
THE GREAT GOMAMON CHARM?
[ PANTING ]
TIME TO GET DOWN TO BUSINESS!
VEEMON, LET'S DO IT!
DIGI-ARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON ARMOR-DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON,
THE FIRE OF COURAGE.
AAH!
FIRE ROCKET!
AAH! AAH! AAH!
GRAA!
YOU HAVE NO SENSE OF HUMOR!
TRY THE KNOCK-KNOCK JOKES.
ARE YOU READY?
YOU BET.
DIGI-ARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR-DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
DIGMON, THE DRILL OF POWER.
ARMOR, HUH? NOT BAD.
UNH.
UNH!
THANKS, DIGMON!
YOU'RE WELCOME.
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
AQUA BLASTERS!
CODY!
AAH!
OHH! OHH!
DON'T WORRY, CODY.
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
[ GROWLS ]
FLAMEDRAMON,
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
AAH! AAH! AAH!
STRIKE THREE!
FLAMEDRAMON CAN HANDLE
THE FRIGIMON BY HIMSELF.
IT'S UP TO US
TO DESTROY THE SPIRE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DO IT FROM THE AIR.
HOLD ON TIGHT, CODY.
UNH. GOLD RUSH!
AAH!
Together: ALL RIGHT!
GRAA!
All: AAH!
Emperor: NO PROBLEM.
I'M NEVER OUT OF IDEAS
OR SLAVES.
EBIDRAMON HERE USES
HIS TWIN-SCISSORS ATTACK
TO CRUSH THE ENEMY
LIKE A SNAIL.
EBIDRAMON,
DESTROY THEM ALL!
Ebidramon: GRAA!
DIGMON!
IF THERE WAS SOME WAY
YOU WERE ABLE TO DIGEVOLVE.
WHAT'S TAKING THEM SO LONG
WITH THAT SPIRE?
STAR SHOWER!
TEMPEST WING!
THEY DID IT! THEY DESTROYED
THE CONTROL SPIRE!
NOW YOU CAN DIGEVOLVE.
WHAT?
HE SAID, "THEY DESTROYED
THE CONTROL SPIRE."
IT'S A FIGURE OF SPEECH!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GOMAMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
IKKAKUMON!
♪ LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
♪ AND SHOW THEM ALL
THE THINGS THAT WE CAN DO ♪
NOW IT'S MY TURN!
GOLD RUSH!
AAH!
YOU GOT HIM!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
♪ TOGETHER ♪
ALL RIGHT, GOMAMON,
YOU'RE IN CHARGE HERE NOW.
GREAT. A FROZEN WASTELAND.
JUST WHAT I ALWAYS WANTED.
AT LEAST YOU'LL HAVE TIME
TO PRACTICE YOUR JOKES.
VERY FUNNY.
WE'D BETTER BE
HEADING BACK HOME.
BEFORE WE GO, THERE'S
ONE THING I HAVE TO FINISH.
REALLY? WHAT'S THAT?
OUR INTRODUCTION.
HELLO, MY NAME'S CODY.
I DON'T GET IT, CODY.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
MY GRANDFATHER SAYS THAT,
NEXT TO PRUNE JUICE,
MANNERS ARE THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING
A MAN CAN HAVE.
CODY REMINDS ME
AN AWFUL LOT OF JOE --
ALWAYS HONEST
AND STICKS TO THE RULES.
HE REMINDS ME OF IZZY --
JUST LOADED WITH CURIOSITY.
PART IZZY AND PART ME?
THAT'S A SCARY COMBINATION.
HE'S GOT
A SPLIT PERSONALITY.
BLAST! THEY'VE DESTROYED
ANOTHER CONTROL SPIRE!
AND THAT WAS
A FRESHLY CONQUERED AREA, TOO!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO GO
TO PLAN "B."
WORMON, WHAT IS PLAN "B"?
WELL?
WE CAN ALL BECOME FRIENDS?
THAT'S NOT PLAN "B,"
YOU FOOL!
DON'T BLAME ME.
I CAN'T SPELL.
T.K.: I'LL BET
HE'S HOME CRYING,
"MOMMY, THOSE MEAN KIDS BROKE
ANOTHER ONE OF MY SPIRES!"
Kari: THE FIGHT'S
NOT OVER YET.
JOE, WILL YOU COME BACK
AND FIGHT WITH US AGAIN?
SURE. MAYBE I'LL FIND
A DIGI-EGG OF MY OWN SOMEDAY,
BUT I HAVE TO
WATCH MY CHOLESTEROL.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU'D
LIKE TO COME TO MY HOUSE.
YOU'D LIKE MY GRANDFATHER,
AND I KNOW HE'D LIKE YOU.
SURE. I LOVE PRUNE JUICE.
IS IT OKAY IF I COME TOO?
IF KARI'S GOING,
I'M GOING, TOO!
Kari: DO YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO DO EVERYTHING I DO?
Davis: YOU AND I ARE PARTNERS!
YOU ALREADY HAVE A PARTNER.
YOU MEAN HIM?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
Davis: IT'S JUST
NOT THE SAME.
All: HA HA HA!
Man: WHERE WILL
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
BUILD HIS NEXT CONTROL SPIRE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."