CHIMERAMON,
THE JIGSAW-PUZZLE DIGIMON,
ATTACKED US INSIDE KEN'S BASE.
THE OTHERS TOOK OFF
WHEN THE FIGHTING SLOWED DOWN,
BUT DEMIVEEMON AND I
WEREN'T ABOUT TO BACK DOWN.
THAT'S WHEN WE RAN
INTO WORMMON.
HE KNEW CHIMERAMON
WAS A HOTHEAD
AND WOULD TURN AGAINST KEN,
PLUS HE WANTED KEN TO GO BACK
TO WHEN HE WASN'T
SUCH AN EVIL JERK,
SO HE AGREED TO HELP US
DESTROY THE BASE.
WHEN WE FOUND THE POWER SOURCE,
IT TURNED INTO
A GOLDEN DIGI-EGG.
THEN THE MOST AMAZING
THING HAPPENED.
VEEMON GOLDEN-ARMOR
DIGIVOLVED INTO MAGNAMON.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
VEEMON,
GOLDEN-ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
MAGNAMON!
WOW, THAT WAS INTENSE!
YOU'RE THE COOLEST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN.
WHERE'D YOU GET THOSE
RAD SHOULDER PADS?
I COULD USE THEM
AS BOOGIE BOARDS.
I AM MAGNAMON,
A GOLDEN-ARMOR DIGIMON
THAT ATTACKS
WITH MY MAGNA BLASTER,
AND I LOOK SO GOOD
DOING IT, TOO.
HMM.
MY STRENGTH IS BACK!
YEAH, ME TOO!
POROMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
UPAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
HAWKMON!
ARMADILLOMON!
I WONDER IF HAWKMON
CAN GOLDEN-ARMOR DIGIVOLVE.
WHERE'D HE COME FROM?
IT CAME FROM THAT
GOLDEN DIGI-EGG.
THIS IS FANTASTIC,
BUT CAN SOMEBODY
TURN OFF HIS HEADLIGHTS?
[ GROWLING ]
HEY, DIGI-FOOLS,
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
YOUR NEW DIGIMON CAN BEAT ME?
HE COULDN'T EVEN
BE MY FLASHLIGHT.
WELL, STICKS AND STONES
CAN BREAK MY BONES,
BUT WHEN MAGNAMON
GETS AHOLD OF YOU,
HE'LL KICK YOUR BUTT.
HE WOULD MAKE
A GOOD NIGHT LIGHT.
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT CAN'T BE GOOD.
HUH?
[ GROWLING ]
CHIMERAMON!
WATCH OUT!
WOW. UHH!
DAVIS, I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THIS.
GO GET HIM, MAGNAMON!
SHOW HIM HE'S NO MATCH
FOR YOU.
IN CASE HE IS,
I'LL GET THE OTHERS.
WE'VE GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE.
SILK THREAD.
I DON'T MEAN
TO DROP IN LIKE THIS,
BUT CHIMERAMON IS TEARING
THE PLACE APART.
NONSENSE! HE'S SIMPLY
FOLLOWING MY ORDERS TO ATTACK.
CHIMERAMON'S NOT FOLLOWING
ANYONE'S ORDERS BUT HIS OWN.
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?
MY GREATEST CREATION
WON'T LET ME DOWN.
[ GROWLING ]
MAGNA PUNCH!
[ ALL PANTING ]
GUYS, WAIT!
RUN, DAVIS!
WHOA!
MAGNA KICK!
WE DON'T HAVE
THAT MUCH TIME.
WE HAVE TO DITCH THIS PLACE
BEFORE IT TAKES A NOSEDIVE.
SURE WOULD BE NICE TO CAPTURE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
RIGHT. LET'S GO GET HIM.
HEAT VAPOR!
AAH!
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE AIMING!
REMEMBER WHO YOUR MASTER IS,
CHIMERAMON.
HA HA HA HA!
MAGNA KICK!
AAH!
[ SHUDDERS ]
I BEGGED YOU TO LISTEN.
HE'S OUT OF CONTROL.
YOU'RE SLIMING UP
MY PANTS!
PLEASE, MASTER,
LET'S LEAVE.
HE'LL DESTROY YOU.
BUT I'M HIS CREATOR.
I NURTURED HIM FROM
THE BEGINNING WITH EVIL.
THESE KIDS TODAY
HAVE NO RESPECT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT OUTSIDE
WHERE IT'S MUCH SAFER.
I'M NOT LEAVING!
I UNDERSTAND. YOU TRIED
TO MAKE CHIMERAMON YOURS,
BUT I'M YOUR TRUE FRIEND.
LISTEN, YOU LITTLE
NIGHT CRAWLER,
IF I HAD A FRIEND,
IT CERTAINLY WOULDN'T BE YOU.
KEN!
WELL, IF IT ISN'T
THE DIGIDESTINED.
I SEE YOU'VE FINALLY
COME TO YOUR SENSES
AND ARE READY TO SURRENDER
TO ME AND CHIMERAMON.
I THINK SOME
OF YOUR HAIR SPRAY
MUST HAVE LEAKED THROUGH
INTO YOUR BRAIN AGAIN.
WHO SAID IT WAS OKAY
FOR YOU TO GO OUT
AND CREATE A DIGIMON ANYWAY?
YEAH, DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DR. FRANKENSTEIN OR SOMETHING,
CREATING CREATURES
JUST FOR YOUR OWN PLEASURE?
CHIMERAMON IS NOT THE MONSTER.
YOU ARE.
LOOK AT THEM.
ARE THEY TRYING TO HURT YOU?
THEY'RE NOT YOUR TOYS
FOR SOME KIND OF A SICK GAME.
THEY'RE ALIVE.
THEY'RE NOT JUST DATA
IN A COMPUTER,
THEY'RE LIVING CREATURES
LIKE YOU AND I.
YOU'RE DIGIDESTINED, TOO,
JUST LIKE US.
YOU HAVE A RESPONSIBILITY
TO BOTH WORLDS.
LIKE WORMMON --
HE'S YOUR FRIEND,
NOT SOMEONE YOU SHOULD
KICK AROUND.
MASTER.
THERE'S ONLY ONE DIGIMON
SUITABLE ENOUGH FOR ME.
HMM?
AND THAT'S CHIMERAMON!
[ GROWLING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
DON'T FEEL TOO PROUD THAT YOU
DESTROYED MY HOME BASE,
BECAUSE YOU ARE GOING DOWN
WITH IT!
WAIT, KEN!
WE WANT TO HELP YOU!
KEN, LISTEN TO ME!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
PARDON ME, BUT IT IS GETTING
A LITTLE HOT DOWN HERE.
RIGHT, BUT DO YOU GUYS HAVE
ENOUGH ENERGY TO DIGIVOLVE?
YES. LET'S LEAVE BEFORE
I'M A FRIED CHICKEN.
THE HEAT IS ON, GUYS.
READY?
MM-HMM.
YEAH.
OKAY,
LET'S DO IT.
All: DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR-DIGIVOLVE TO...
DIGMON,
THE DRILL OF KNOWLEDGE!
I USED TO SAY
THE DRILL OF POWER,
BUT I THINK THIS
MAKES ME SOUND SMARTER.
HAWKMON,
ARMOR-DIGIVOLVE TO...
HALSEMON,
THE WINGS OF LOVE!
GATOMON,
ARMOR-DIGIVOLVE TO...
NEFERTIMON,
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT!
PATAMON,
ARMOR-DIGIVOLVE TO...
PEGASUSMON,
FLYING HOPE!
GOLD RUSH!
MAGNA BLAST!
[ GROWLING ]
AAH!
GOLD RUSH!
COME ON, EVERYONE,
FOLLOW ME.
I'LL FOLLOW HIM.
I'LL FOLLOW YOU.
NOW, THAT'S WHAT I CALL
FOLLOWING ORDERS.
DUDES,
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
[ ROARS ]
OH, THE HUMANITY.
MAGNA BLAST!
AAH!
[ ROARS ]
IT'S NO USE.
HE'S TOO STRONG.
I'M RUNNING OUT OF POWER.
[ GROWLING ]
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA!
THAT'S IT,
LET HIM HAVE IT, CHIMERAMON.
YOU CAN DO IT, MAGNAMON.
SILENCE!
I HOPE YOU'RE FINALLY
PROUD OF YOURSELF.
[ GROWLS ]
YOU'VE OFFICIALLY
BECOME WORSE
THAN THE MONSTERS
YOU'VE CREATED.
WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO THAT SWEET KID I MET
A LONG TIME AGO
WHO HAD A DREAM
TO TAKE OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD?
SURE, IT WAS
A SICK AND TWISTED DREAM,
BUT STILL, WE HAD
A LOT OF LAUGHS TOGETHER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE BOY
I WAS PROUD TO CALL "MASTER"?
OF COURSE,
YOU MADE ME CALL YOU THAT.
[ GROWLING ]
TAKE IT EASY.
I'M NOT A MELON.
YOU'VE CHANGED, BUT IT'S
NOT TOO LATE FOR YOU.
YOU STARTED CAPTURING DIGIMON
AND YOU TURNED THEM
INTO YOUR SLAVES
INSTEAD OF INTO YOUR FRIENDS.
I DIDN'T AGREE,
BUT I STUCK BY YOUR SIDE
BECAUSE I WAS YOUR DIGIMON.
AND THEN YOU STARTED
BEING CRUEL TO ME,
THE ONE WHO KNOWS
THE TRUE YOU.
THE OTHERS MAY KNOW
AND FEAR YOU
AS THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
BUT NEVER FORGET
THAT I KNOW THE REAL YOU.
HUH? WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I'LL ALWAYS THINK OF YOU
FOR YOUR KINDNESS, KEN,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
ONE DAY I HOPE YOU'LL REALIZE
THAT THE REAL KEN
ISN'T THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
BUT THE KEN THAT'S MY FRIEND.
HUH?
AND ONLY A REAL FRIEND
WOULD DO THIS.
AAH!
UHH! UHH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLING ]
WORMMON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAGNAMON,
IT'S UP TO YOU NOW.
[ GROWLING ]
WORMMON!
PLEASE, MAGNAMON,
SAVE KEN FOR ME.
HERE'S WHAT LITTLE ENERGY
I HAVE LEFT. USE IT.
[ GASPING ]
WORMMON'S POWER
HAS RE-ENERGIZED ME.
MAGNA EXPLOSION!
AAH!
I HATE IT
WHEN THIS HAPPENS!
[ ALL GASP ]
[ CHEERING ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY DEFEATED ME.
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
ARE YOU OKAY?
HEY.
YOU WERE AWESOME!
HUH?
WAIT A SECOND.
DID SOMEONE
LOSE THEIR KEYS?
[ GASPS ]
I LOST. I'M A FAILURE.
THIS ISN'T WHAT
WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
I WAS FLAWLESS.
MY PLANS WERE SUPPOSED TO
WORK OUT PERFECTLY.
HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
THEY MUST HAVE CHEATED
SOMEHOW.
THAT'S THE ONLY
POSSIBLE EXPLANATION.
I ONLY HAVE ONE CHOICE LEFT,
AND THAT'S JUST
TO CHEAT MYSELF.
I'LL START OVER.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO RESET
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
RESET THE DIGITAL WORLD?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, KEN?
IT'S SIMPLE.
I'LL JUST GO HOME
AND DELETE ALL
THE DIGITAL WORLD DATA
OFF MY COMPUTER
AND CREATE A NEW PROGRAM,
THAT WAY I CAN START
A NEW DIGITAL WORLD
THAT DOESN'T CHEAT.
THE DIGITAL WORLD IS
A COMPLETELY REAL PLACE, KEN.
IT'S NOT JUST SOMETHING
THAT'S PROGRAMMED
INTO YOUR COMPUTER.
WE TRIED TO
TELL YOU THAT BEFORE,
BUT YOU THOUGHT
WE WERE TRYING
TO PLAY SOME KIND
OF A TRICK ON YOU.
Cody: THIS ISN'T SOME KIND
OF A VIDEO GAME.
KEN, DIGIMON ARE REAL,
AND IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU REALIZED WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN DOING.
WHAT?
YOU'VE BEEN HURTING
INNOCENT CREATURES, KEN.
YOU DIGIMON WERE ALL
AT THE SOCCER GAME
IN THE REAL WORLD.
I REMEMBER NOW.
YOU ARE REAL,
NOT JUST COMPUTER DATA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
I NEVER FIGURED THAT OUT.
FOR AN EVIL GENIUS,
YOU REALLY ARE
A SLOW LEARNER, KEN.
AND YOU'VE CONSTANTLY
BEEN ABUSING DIGIMON
EVER SINCE YOU CLAIMED
TO BE THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
I HAD NO IDEA.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I THOUGHT MY DARK RINGS
WERE A STROKE OF GENIUS.
I NEVER REALIZED
I WAS CAUSING PAIN.
I MADE THEM WORK FOR ME
TIRELESSLY
WITHOUT EVER
GIVING THEM A BREAK,
AND I WAS CRUEL TO THEM
BEYOND IMAGINATION.
I'M A MONSTER!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT I'VE DONE!
IT'S HARD TO ARGUE
WITH YOU THERE, KEN.
YOU'VE DONE SOME
PRETTY HORRIBLE STUFF.
THE IMPORTANT THIS IS
YOU'VE REALIZED
WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
TO MAKE A FRESH START.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
[ CRYING ]
[ GASP ]
WORMMON!
WORMMON?
HE'S STILL BREATHING.
YOU'VE RETURNED
TO YOUR OLD SELF.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT, KEN.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR ME.
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE
TO BE SORRY.
WORMMON'S ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT, KEN.
HUH?
WHERE'D YOU GET
THAT THING, DAVIS?
I FOUND IT
IN THE SAND. WHY?
IT LOOKS LIKE ONE
OF THE CRESTS
WE USED TO HAVE
IN THE OLD DAYS.
YOU'RE RIGHT, T.K.,
AND IT HAS THE CREST
OF KINDNESS ON IT.
BUT WHY IS IT COMING TO ME?
BECAUSE IT BELONGS
TO YOU, KEN.
IT'S THE CREST
OF KINDNESS.
THERE MUST BE SOME MISTAKE.
I'VE BEEN ANYTHING BUT KIND.
THAT'S WHAT WIZARDMON MEANT
WHEN HE TOLD US
THAT KINDNESS WOULD RELEASE
THE GOLDEN RADIANCE.
KEN MUST BE THE KEY
TO UNLOCKING THE POWER.
I TOLD YOU THAT DEEP INSIDE
YOU WERE KIND.
WORMMON...
I'M SORRY.
DON'T GO.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND, TOO.
GOODBYE, KEN.
WORMMON, NO!
HE'S GONE, KEN.
HE CAN'T BE!
NOT AGAIN.
WORMMON'S GONE,
JUST LIKE MY BROTHER.
I WAS HELPLESS TO SAVE HIM,
AND NOW I CAN'T SAVE
WORMMON, EITHER.
[ CRYING ]
WHY DO I KEEP LOSING PEOPLE?
I CAME TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
TO GET AWAY
FROM ALL THOSE FEELINGS,
BUT I JUST CAN'T ESCAPE.
KEN, WE MISS YOU.
THERE'S STILL PEOPLE
WHO LOVE YOU.
I GOT TO GO.
DON'T WALK AWAY
FROM YOUR PROBLEMS.
LET US HELP YOU, KEN.
YOU'RE DIGIDESTINED!
JOIN US!
Cody: I WONDER
WHERE HE'S GOING.
I HOPE HE'LL BE OKAY.
HEY, MATT, I MADE IT!
OH, NO, SHE FOLLOWED US.
SHE'S LIKE A BOOMERANG
THAT KEEPS COMING BACK.
IT'S FUNNY,
BUT WHEN YOU DROVE OFF
WITH YOUR TIRES SCREECHING,
YOU DIDN'T REALIZE
YOU LEFT ME STANDING THERE.
MY BAD. SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I MUST HAVE FORGOT.
OH, WHERE ARE DAVIS
AND THE OTHERS?
I THINK TAI KNOWS.
HEY, TAI, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THE OTHERS WENT?
LET ME THINK ABOUT THAT
FOR A SEC.
UH, IZZY, WEREN'T YOU
THE LAST ONE TO SEE THEM?
[ STUTTERS ]
OF COURSE.
I'LL GO FIND THEM
RIGHT NOW.
HUH?
OH, BOY, WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
THE DIGIPORT IS OPENING.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
DID YOU GUYS
HEAR THAT NOISE?
IT COULD BE
A WILD ANIMAL.
YEAH, THE WOODS
ARE A DANGEROUS PLACE.
YOU BETTER LEAVE QUICK.
I'LL TELL DAVIS
YOU STOPPED BY.
THERE THEY ARE.
JUNE, WHO INVITED YOU
TO COME OUT HERE?
MATT DID.
HEY, GUYS, WAIT FOR ME!
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
WOULD IT BE OKAY
TO GET A RIDE HOME?
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE
THE BUS BY MYSELF.
NO WAY!
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS!
IT'S NOT MY FAULT YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
COME ON, THAT'S NOT NICE.
SOMEONE TAKE THE BUS
WITH JUNE.
THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU,
AND I ALREADY HAVE
THE PERFECT VOLUNTEER IN MIND.
AND THE ABSOLUTE PERFECT
VOLUNTEER IS T.K.
MATT, YOU TAKE
THE BUS HOME WITH JUNE.
HUH? I'M BROKE.
THERE'S MORE
THAN ENOUGH HERE.
HAVE FUN, YOU TWO.
HAVE HER HOME
BEFORE CURFEW.
I'LL TRADE FOR YOUR SEAT.
DON'T BE SILLY.
YOU'LL SIT WITH ME.
AAH!
COME ON, HUNK, WE'D BETTER
GO CATCH THE BUS.
IT'S A LONG RIDE.
PLEASE, T.K., YOU CAN
HAVE MY COLLEGE MONEY.
AAH!
SEE YOU IN FOUR HOURS!
I GIVE UP.
THE MISSING BOY GENIUS
KEN ICHIJOUJI
MYSTERIOUSLY RETURNED HOME
AFTER BEING MISSING
FOR THE LAST SEVERAL MONTHS.
EVENTS SURROUNDING
HIS PUZZLING DISAPPEARANCE
AND SUDDEN REAPPEARANCE
ARE STILL UNCLEAR,
BUT HIS FAMILY IS THANKFUL
TO HAVE HIM HOME AND SAFE.
LOOKS LIKE THE DIGIWORLD
WILL BE A SAFER PLACE
FROM NOW ON WITHOUT KEN
RUNNING THE SHOW.
YEAH, THAT SURE
MUST HAVE BEEN SOME BATTLE
THESE GUYS FOUGHT.
I THINK WE OLDER KIDS
CAN TAKE A LOT OF PRIDE
WHEN WE CALL THESE BEGINNERS
THE NEW DIGIDESTINED.
YOU'RE RIGHT, IZZY.
THE TORCH HAS BEEN PASSED,
AND THEY DIDN'T
GET BURNED ONCE.
[ CRYING ]
MY LITTLE BOY IS BACK.
FIRST WE LOST
HIS BROTHER,
THEN WE LOST KEN.
I'M JUST SO GLAD
HE'S BACK HOME.
HOW WILL KEN USE
THE CREST OF KINDNESS?
FIND OUT
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."