RUN FOR YOUR LIVES
IT'S THE EVIL DIGIMON EMPEROR
AAH!
[ NEIGHING ]
THAT WAS CLOSE.
AAH!
Woman: YOU'RE GOING TO BE
LATE FOR SCHOOL, T.K.
HURRY UP
AND FINISH YOUR BREAKFAST.
NEW SCHOOL,
NEW APARTMENT,
BUT THE SAME OLD
LUMPY OATMEAL.
I'M DONE, MOM,
I'M LEAVING.
SORRY I CAN'T DRIVE YOU
ON YOUR FIRST DAY.
I HAVE TO WRITE THIS ARTICLE
BEFORE THE DEADLINE
ABOUT THE HISTORICAL
SIGNIFICANCE OF TOILET PAPER.
IT'S OKAY. I'LL WALK.
SEE YOU LATER.
OH!
HOW'S IT GOING?
FINE, THANK YOU.
GREAT. MY NAME'S T.K.,
AND MY MOM AND I
JUST MOVED INTO THIS BUILDING.
I'M IN SEVENTH GRADE,
CLASS "A." NICE TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS YOLEI.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO WALK
TO SCHOOL WITH US?
IT TAKES 12.3 MINUTES
IF THERE'S NO WIND.
IT'LL BE FUN.
OH, AND THIS IS CODY.
WELCOME
TO THE BUILDING, T.K.
WE DON'T WANT
TO BE LATE.
LET'S DO IT.
HEY, YOLEI, CAN YOU COME OVER
AFTER SCHOOL
AND FIX MY COMPUTER AGAIN?
ONLY IF YOUR MOM
MAKES THOSE BROWNIES I LOVE.
I'LL SEND AN E-MAIL
AND ASK HER
IF SHE'LL MAKE A BATCH.
IT'S A DEAL. PERFECTO!
Boy: KICK IT OVER HERE!
HUH?
TAI? I'M SEEING THINGS.
Boy: HERE YOU GO, DAVIS!
OHH!
THANKS. GREAT CATCH.
HUH?
YOU LOOK FAMILIAR.
MUST BE THE GOGGLES.
HEY, DAVIS,
YOU'RE HOLDING UP THE GAME.
YEAH!
WHAT AM I THINKING?
THAT CAN'T BE TAI.
HE'S A MUCH BETTER
SOCCER PLAYER THAN THAT KID.
Girl: I GOT IT.
I GOT IT.
COME ON! PASS IT!
[ BELL RINGS ]
ALL RIGHT! WHAT LUCK.
YOU'RE IN MY CLASS
AGAIN, KARI.
I WOULDN'T CALL THAT LUCK.
HEY, THE WEIRDEST THING
JUST HAPPENED.
THIS NEW KID SAID
I REMINDED HIM OF SOMEONE.
PROBABLY THINKS
I'M A MOVIE STAR.
TAI, HELP!
TAI!
HUH?
I'M MR. HAMASAKI.
I'LL BE YOUR TEACHER.
I'D LIKE YOU ALL
TO WELCOME A NEW STUDENT.
WHOA!
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M T.K.
IT'S THAT KID.
Mr. Hamasaki: PLEASE TAKE A SEAT
NEXT TO THE GIRL
WITH THE CAMERA
AROUND HER NECK.
TOGETHER AGAIN.
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
[ Thinking ] THAT KID'S TRYING
TO MAKE A MOVE ON MY GIRL.
OUR TEACHER LOOKS
LIKE OGREMON.
NO! NO!
AAH!
HURRY! DON'T LET
SNIMON CATCH US!
THIS PRAYING MANTIS DIGIMON
CAN CUT THROUGH ANYTHING
WITH HIS
TWIN SICKLES ATTACK!
TWIN SICKLES!
AAH!
OH, NO!
BIYOMON! TENTOMON!
AGUMON.
TAI, YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO DIGEVOLVE.
[ BEEPING ]
HUH?
THAT'S WHY I NEED
YOUR HELP, TAI. I CAN'T.
DID YOU FORGET HOW?
IT'S LIKE RIDING A BICYCLE.
NOW START PEDALING
AND DIGEVOLVE!
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
IT'S NO USE.
AS LONG AS I HAVE
THE BLACK DIGIVICE,
THERE'S NO WAY
THEY CAN DIGEVOLVE.
HA HA HA HA HA!
GRAAH!
MOVE YOUR TAIL!
[ GASPS ]
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
MORE HELP.
I'D BETTER CONTACT
THE OTHERS.
"COME TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
THE DIGIMON NEED OUR HELP."
MUST BE AN ONLINE GAME.
LET'S SEE WHO SENT IT.
TAI KAMIYA.
THERE'S A GIRL
WITH THE SAME LAST NAME.
THIS E-MAIL'S
PROBABLY HERS.
T.K., HOW DOES YOUR MOM
LIKE THE NEW APARTMENT?
SHE'S BEEN ON THE COMPUTER
THE WHOLE TIME.
HEY, BUDDY.
HIS NAME IS NOT BUDDY.
IT'S T.K.
ALL RIGHT, T.J. OR J.B.
OR WHATEVER IT IS,
HOW DO YOU KNOW KARI?
HUH? HOW DO I KNOW HER?
OH, I GET IT.
YOU'RE JEALOUS OF ME.
I'M NOT JEALOUS
OF ANYBODY!
HEY!
OH, HI, YOLEI.
YOU'RE KARI KAMIYA,
AREN'T YOU?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
WELL, ARE YOU
RELATED TO TAI?
HE SENT THIS E-MAIL.
MY BROTHER NEEDS US.
[ PANTING ]
Yolei: IZZY!
YOLEI, I NEED TO USE
THE COMPUTER ROOM RIGHT AWAY.
THE LEGENDARY FORMER
COMPUTER CLUB PRESIDENT
IS ACTUALLY LOOKING FOR ME?
I'M HONORED.
WHAT'S UP, IZZY?
TAI SENT US
AN URGENT E-MAIL.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I GOT ONE, TOO.
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO SEND TAI AN ANSWER
WHEN THE BATTERY RAN OUT
ON MY COMPUTER.
I KNEW I SHOULD HAVE
RECHARGED IT AFTER I PLAYED
TRIGONOMETRY TRIVIA
ON THE INTERNET LAST NIGHT,
BUT BOY, TALK ABOUT FUN.
I GOT HIM!
IT'S FROM IZZY.
HE'S GOT KARI
AND T.K. WITH HIM.
Agumon: TAI,
COME HERE, QUICK!
WHAT'S THE DIGITAL WORLD?
IS THAT A NEW AMUSEMENT PARK?
I BET THEY HAVE
SOME GREAT RIDES.
TAI SAID THERE WERE
A LOT OF DIGIMON THERE,
WHATEVER THEY ARE.
YOU KNOW TAI?
Kari: THEY PLAY
ON THE SAME SOCCER TEAM.
HEY, GUYS,
I'VE GOT AN IDEA. LET'S ALL
GO TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
YOLEI, WEREN'T YOU
COMING OVER?
REMEMBER, YOU WERE GOING
TO FIX MY COMPUTER.
OH, SORRY, I FORGOT.
IF TAI'S THERE, THE GATE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD'S OPEN.
LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S GOT THE CREST OF COURAGE
ON IT. IS IT AN EGG?
I NEVER SAW AN EGG
WITH A SPIKE IN IT.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN ROUGH
ON THE CHICKEN
THAT LAID THAT THING.
LET'S HAVE A CLOSER LOOK
AT THIS THING.
AAH!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
OH, THEY LOOK
LIKE FIREFLIES...
REALLY FAST ONES.
YOU DID PROMISE.
I KNOW.
WE'RE GOING BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
Davis: I'M GOING
WITH YOU.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
NOT JUST ANYBODY CAN GO.
YOU NEED A DIGIVICE.
LISTEN, T.C.,
IF YOU CAN GO, SO CAN I.
HUH?
AAH!
[ BOTH GASP ]
WHAT'S THIS?
A DIGIVICE.
IT'S A DIFFERENT MODEL
THAN THE ONES WE HAVE.
Izzy: WE'D BETTER GO NOW,
WHILE THE GATE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS OPEN.
YEAH, BUT HOW LONG
WILL IT STAY OPEN FOR?
I DON'T CARE. I'M GOING
TO HELP MY BROTHER.
CAN I GET DONKEY MADNESS
ON THIS THING?
IT'S NOT A GAME.
IF THE DIGITAL WORLD
SENT YOU A DIGIVICE,
THERE'S A REASON, AND YOU
SHOULD TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
I'M NOT WAITING
ANY LONGER.
I'M WITH YOU.
[ MOANS ]
IT'S YOUR TURN,
UNLESS YOU'RE SCARED.
HUH?
I'M THERE!
HMM.
WHOA!
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
HUH? NOTHING. HA HA HA.
BUT IZZY,
WHAT WAS THAT LIGHT?
UH, THE COMPUTER MUST NEED
A NEW SCREEN SAVER. HA HA.
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-OH ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-OH ♪
Davis: WHOA! MY FIRST TIME
BEING DOWNLOADED.
PRETTY COOL.
SO THIS IS
THE DIGITAL WORLD, HUH?
WOW. THIS PLACE COMES
WITH A NEW WARDROBE.
HMM.
LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE SOME VISITORS
IN MY GARDEN
AND THEY WEREN'T EVEN
ON THE GUEST LIST.
IT'S OVER THIS WAY.
THIS PLACE DOESN'T SEEM
SO SCARY.
THE WAY TAI PUT IT,
THERE WERE MONSTERS
EVERYWHERE. HUH?
HEY, GUYS, CHECK IT OUT.
THERE'S A VENDING MACHINE.
I AM A LITTLE THIRSTY.
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ SCREAMING ]
HA HA HA!
HA HA. VERY FUNNY.
SO, WERE THOSE THINGS
DIGIMON?
YEP, THERE'S TONS
OF OTHER ONES, TOO,
A LOT CUTER THAN THOSE.
A LOT SCARIER ONES, TOO.
DO THEY ALL COME
OUT OF VENDING MACHINES?
THEY'RE REAL CLOSE BY.
THERE!
T.K.!
PATAMON!
BOY, AM I GLAD TO SEE YOU!
HA HA HA!
HI, GUYS. I'M GLAD
YOU ALL MADE IT.
TAI! I TOLD THOSE GUYS
YOU'D BE ALL RIGHT.
UH, DAVIS,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
KARI!
HA HA HA! GATOMON!
[ Gasps ] YOUR TAIL RING!
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED.
HORNBLASTER!
Gatomon: ONE DAY
THIS BOSSY HUMAN APPEARED
AND BEGAN MAKING DIGIMON
INTO HIS SLAVES.
HE SAID, "I AM
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR."
I HEARD WE'RE ALL GOING TO
HAVE TO PUNCH
A TIME CLOCK, TOO.
T.K.: ANOTHER HUMAN?
YOU MEAN THAT SOMEONE ELSE
COMES HERE BESIDES US?
WELL, THERE GOES
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
YEAH, AND HE'S GOT THIS
STRANGE NEW DARK DIGIVICE
THAT MAKES US UNABLE
TO DIGEVOLVE.
SHOW HER YOURS.
HUH? LIKE THIS ONE?
THAT'S IT! YOU WORK
FOR THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
WHAT? I DON'T WORK
FOR ANYBODY.
BESIDES, MINE'S NOT DARK.
I GOT THIS WHEN IT CAME OUT
OF THE COMPUTER.
[ Thinking ] SO THAT'S
WHAT CAME OUT OF THE EGG
WHEN I PICKED IT UP --
THREE NEW DIGIVICES,
BUT WHY DID DAVIS GET ONE?
WHAT'S HIS PURPOSE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY, WHO GOT
THE OTHER TWO DIGIVICES?
WHERE DID EVERYONE
DISAPPEAR TO, IZZY?
I-I TOLD YOU ALREADY, YOLEI.
THEY WENT HOME.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU
OFF THE HOOK.
I KNOW YOU'RE HIDING
SOMETHING FROM ME.
WHAT IS THE DIGITAL WORLD,
AND WHAT ARE DIGIMON?
I-I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THEN WHAT
DO YOU CALL THIS?
[ Gasps ]
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
CODY HAS GOT ONE AS WELL.
WE HAVE TO STAY AFTER SCHOOL
FOR COMPUTER CLUB,
BUT SINCE YOU MADE
THE BROWNIES,
I'LL COME HOME
AND PICK THEM UP.
THE DARK DIGIVICE
IS DRAINING OUR POWER
AND MAKING US ALL WEAK
AS NEWBORN KITTENS.
THAT'S WHY
YOU COULDN'T DIGEVOLVE.
YEAH, IF I COULD DIGEVOLVE,
HE WOULDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR USES
THESE POWERFUL DARK RINGS
TO CONTROL THE DIGIMON.
Patamon:
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT,
AND ONCE THE RING
CAPTURES YOU,
YOU'RE A SLAVE FOR LIFE.
THESE COLLARS DO EVERYTHING
BUT GET RID OF FLEAS.
I'M GOING TO SLAP
A DARK RING ON HIM.
HA HA HA!
OH, YOU THINK SO, DO YOU?
WELL, THIS IS JUST
A CAME TO ME,
AND I'M AFRAID IF YOU CAN'T
PLAY BY MY RULES,
I'M JUST GOING TO
HAVE TO DISQUALIFY YOU.
HMM, WHO WILL DESTROY YOU?
EENIE, MEENIE, MINIE, MON.
ATTACK, MONOCHROMON!
[ ROARS ]
LOOKS LIKE
A DEFLATED BEACH BALL.
NO WONDER, IT'S GOT
A SPIKE THROUGH IT.
YEAH, PLUS IT'S HEAVIER
THAN MY MOM'S MEAT LOAF.
[ GROANS ]
IT WON'T BUDGE.
MOVE ASIDE.
THIS IS A WOMAN'S JOB.
[ GROANS ]
T.K.: TOO BAD WE DON'T HAVE
A WOMAN HERE TO HELP.
GUYS, I PUMP IRON
ALL THE TIME.
LET ME DO IT.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
LIGHT AS A FEATHER.
YOU GUYS NEED TO WORK OUT
A LITTLE MORE.
THERE'S A PROBLEM.
WHOA!
YAHOO! FREE AT LAST!
FREE AT LAST!
YOU MOVED THAT DIGIEGG!
MY NAME'S VEEMON.
YOU CAN JUST CALL ME VEEMON.
HI. I'M DAVIS.
I'VE HEARD OF VEEMON.
SUPPOSEDLY, HE'S A FUN-LOVING,
ADVENTURE-SEEKING LITTLE DIGIMON
THAT BRINGS YOU GOOD LUCK,
BUT I THOUGHT
HE WAS JUST A LEGEND.
NOPE. I'M REAL, ALL RIGHT,
AND I'VE BEEN WAITING
A VERY LONG TIME
TO MEET YOU, DAVIS.
I THINK YOU GOT
THE WRONG GUY.
YOU'RE THE ONE
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO WAS ABLE TO MOVE
THE DIGIEGG OF COURAGE.
[ Thinking ] THAT'S RIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH
I HAVE THE CREST OF COURAGE,
I COULDN'T MOVE THE DIGIEGG,
BUT DAVIS COULD.
AAH!
WHAT'S THAT,
AN EARTHQUAKE?
NO, LOOK UP THERE!
IT'S A MONSTER!
NO, THAT'S A DIGIMON!
MONOCHROMON!
T.K.: MONOCHROMON -- HIS SHELL
IS HARDER THAN DIAMONDS.
HIS ATTACK -- VOLCANIC STRIKE --
SENDS OUT MILLIONS OF FIREBALLS.
BOOM-BA-BA-POP!
PEPPER BREATH.
VOLCANIC STRIKE!
[ Gasps ] COME ON,
LET'S GO!
DAVIS!
AAH!
DAVIS, HURRY UP
AND OPEN THE DIGIEGG!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
Tai: DAVIS,
GET DOWN HERE.
AAH!
DAVIS, TELL ME,
WHAT HURTS?
EVERYTHING BUT MY EARLOBES.
YOU CONTROL
THE DIGIEGG OF COURAGE.
YOU'VE GOT
TO USE YOUR COURAGE
TO OPEN IT UP.
DAVIS, GET UP.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
OH, OKAY.
I CAN DIGEVOLVE
IF YOU OPEN THE EGG.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE COURAGE
TO DO IT.
IT'S WORTH A TRY.
WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
KARI.
I CAN'T MOVE MY ANKLE.
WE'RE SITTING DUCKS HERE.
All: AAH!
DAVIS!
HAVE COURAGE!
KARI'S IN TROUBLE!
[ GASPS ]
YOU WANT COURAGE?
I'LL SHOW YOU COURAGE.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE.
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE?
HUH?
WHOA! WHAT'S THAT?
I AM FLAMEDRAMON.
AS VEEMON, I USE
THE DIGIEGG OF COURAGE
TO ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
MY FIRE ROCKET ATTACK
WILL CHARBROIL THE ENEMY
LIKE A WELL-DONE STEAK.
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE, HUH?
AGAINST THE POWER
OF MY DARK DIGIVICE,
THE SHOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO DIGEVOLVE AT ALL.
HMM, THEY'RE MORE RESOURCEFUL
THAN I THOUGHT.
VOLCANIC STRIKE!
[ GASPING ]
FIRE ROCKET!
BARBECUE THAT DARK DREAM,
FLAMEDRAMON!
WHOA!
OH, WOW.
WHAT'S THIS?
HUH?
THAT'S A GOOD MONOCHROMON.
YOU SUMMONED ME,
MY EVIL EMPEROR.
I BELIEVE
THAT WE FOUND OURSELVES
A WORTHY FOE AT LAST.
GREAT.
JUST ONE QUESTION --
WHAT'S A FOE?
GOODBYE, MONOCHROMON.
DON'T FORGET TO WRITE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
CAN TURN SUCH A NICE DIGIMON
INTO SUCH A NASTY CREATURE.
NICE WORKING WITH YOU.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN SOMETIME.
HEY, GUYS, THAT ARMOR
DIGEVOLVING WAS PRETTY COOL.
EVEN THOUGH THE REST OF US
CAN'T DIGEVOLVE,
I KNOW THAT YOU NEW GUYS
WILL BE ABLE TO DEFEAT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
WITH NO PROBLEM.
YEAH. LEAVE IT TO ME.
DAVIS, I THINK YOU WERE
REALLY BRAVE BACK THERE,
BUT I NOTICED THAT
YOU BROKE YOUR GOGGLES,
AND AS WE ALL KNOW,
THE LEADER OF THE DIGIDESTINED
JUST WOULDN'T LOOK RIGHT
WITHOUT THEM, SO HERE --
I WANT YOU TO HAVE MINE.
WOW.
THEY LOOK REAL CUTE.
GOOD, THE SUN'S GOING DOWN.
NOW WE CAN RELAX.
T.K.: WHY IS THAT?
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
NEVER APPEARS AT NIGHT.
EXCUSE ME, TAI,
BUT IT IS GETTING LATE.
DON'T YOU GUYS
NEED TO GO HOME SOON?
WE DO, BUT I'M NOT SURE
IF WE CAN GET HOME.
BE CAREFUL.
NEVER STAY TOO LONG.
Yolei: CODY'S BACK. CAN WE GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD NOW?
Izzy: IT'S NOT SAFE.
Cody: AT LEAST
I GOT THE BROWNIES.
THIS IS THE BEST THING
I'VE EVER TASTED!
Yolei: WHAT DOES IT MEAN
WHEN THE LIGHT
ON THAT THING GOES ON?
WHAT THING?
THAT THING
ON THE COMPUTER.
AAH!
HEY, GUYS, LET ME IN!
IT'S DAVIS!
YOU DON'T SEE THAT
EVERY DAY.
All: AAH!
Cody: GET OFF!
YOU'RE CRUSHING MY BROWNIES!
WHILE DAVIS AND THE OTHERS
HAVE RETURNED
TO THE REAL WORLD,
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
WAS PLANNING HIS NEXT ATTACK.
CAN THE DIGIDESTINED STOP HIM?
A NEW ADVENTURE
HAS JUST BEGUN
ON "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."