Cody: CAN YOU BELIEVE OWIKAWA
USED TO BE MY DAD'S BEST FRIEND?
GRANDPA KNEW ARMADILLOMON
WAS A DIGIMON
BECAUSE DAD AND OWIKAWA HAD SEEN
THE DIGITAL WORLD YEARS AGO.
OWIKAWA IS DESPERATE TO GO
TO THE DIGIWORLD,
AND SOMEHOW HE'S PLANNING TO USE
THE DARK BLOOMS TO GET THERE.
GRANDPA TRIED TO CONVINCE
OWIKAWA TO BE GOOD AGAIN.
IT DIDN'T WORK!
THEN BLACK WARGREYMON SHOWED UP
TO FIGHT WITH OWIKAWA
AND WAS HURT PRETTY BADLY,
BUT BEFORE HE WAS COMPLETELY
RECONFIGURED,
BLACK WARGREYMON SACRIFICED
HIMSELF TO SEAL THE GATE.
IT WAS HORRIBLE,
AND IT WAS WONDERFUL.
I TOLD HIM
HE HAD A HEART.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Yolei: WELL, THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO BE THE MEETING PLACE.
Davis: YEAH,
BUT NO ONE'S EVEN HERE.
Kari: WAIT, LOOK,
THERE'S ONE OF THEM NOW!
Izzy: AND THERE'S
ANOTHER ONE, TOO.
Cody: THEY SEEM TO BE WAITING
FOR SOMETHING.
Kari: DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE WAITING FOR OWIKAWA?
Yolei: I WONDER IF THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE ALL HERE.
Cody:
THAT WOULD MAKE SENSE.
MAYBE THIS'LL BE OUR CHANCE
TO CAPTURE HIM.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE, GUYS,
LET'S NOT RUSH INTO ANYTHING.
BUT WHY ARE THEY
AT HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE?
A GATE TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
HAS BEEN OPENED
IN THIS LOCATION
MANY TIMES BEFORE.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
THEY'RE HERE.
BUT ACCORDING TO WHAT
GATOMON AND THE OTHERS SAID,
BLACK WARGREYMON COMPLETELY
SEALED THE GATE
BETWEEN THE WORLDS, UNLESS THOSE
CHILDREN DON'T KNOW THAT YET.
Cody: THEN OWIKAWA DOESN'T,
EITHER.
Davis: HEY, T.K.!
Cody: SHH! BIG MOUTH!
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
TAI AND SORA ARE?
THEY'RE KEEPING AN EYE
ON THAT GIRL FROM YESTERDAY
TO MAKE SURE NOTHING HAPPENS
TO HER.
Tai: BE VERY QUIET,
AGUMON.
WE CAN'T LET HER KNOW
WE'RE HERE.
Agumon: I AM BEING
VERY QUIET.
BUT YOU'RE NOT BEING VERY
INVISIBLE. GET BACK HERE!
Agumon: BEING A SPY
WOULD BE EASIER
IF WE DIDN'T HAVE TO DO
SO MUCH SPYING.
DOES IT BOTHER YOU THAT SORA'S
WITH TAI INSTEAD OF YOU?
COME ON,
TAI'S MY BEST FRIEND,
AND HE KNOWS
HOW I FEEL.
BESIDES, I COMPLETELY
TRUST SORA.
I'M NOT WORRIED AT ALL,
IZZY.
[ CELLULAR PHONE RINGS ]
HELLO?
HI, IZZY HONEY,
IT'S MOM.
I'M DOWN
AT HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE.
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST
THINKING ABOUT THE FACT
THAT ALL THE OTHER PARENTS
ARE DOING THEIR PART
TO HELP OUT
ALL OF YOU KIDS --
YOU KNOW, EACH ONE LENDING
THEIR OWN EXPERTISE.
SO I SAT RIGHT DOWN
AND ASKED MYSELF,
NOW, WHAT'S MY EXPERTISE?
AND THE ANSWER IS SNACKS!
SO I MADE YOU GUYS SOME PB&J
WITH THE CRUST CUT OFF.
PB&J?
BUT, MOM...
IZZY, I KNOW HOW
YOU HATE THE CRUSTS.
AW, OKAY, HOLD ON.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OKAY. BYE.
MY MOM.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, GUYS.
PB&J!
YEE-HAW!
DON'T YOU THINK THAT EVERYTHING
ABOUT THE DIGITAL WORLD
JUST SEEMS TO BE GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE?
I MEAN,
WE DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
OF WHAT OWIKAWA'S PLANNING,
OR WHAT THAT SHADOW
THAT CAME OUT OF HIM WAS,
OR EVEN IF HE'S MORE
THAN AN ORDINARY HUMAN.
I WONDER IF THERE'S REALLY
ANYTHING WE CAN DO
TO SAVE ALL THOSE CHILDREN.
I DON'T KNOW, BUT WE'VE JUST
GOT TO BELIEVE IN OURSELVES
AND KEEP TRYING.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I GUESS
I'M JUST FEELING NERVOUS.
I JUST WISH WE KNEW
WHAT OWIKAWA WAS PLANNING.
THE TIME FOR HARVESTING
HAS COME.
Mummymon: OH, NO,
LOOK AT THAT!
IT'S THOSE PESKY KIDS!
THEY'RE GUARDING THEM!
HUH? WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
KEN?
NOTHING. I THOUGHT
I FELT SOMETHING.
WAS IT OWIKAWA?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
MAYBE MY MIND
WAS PLAYING TRICKS ON ME.
I SURE HOPE SO.
Davis: YEAH,
I HOPE SO, TOO.
DO YOU THINK
THEY NOTICED US?
WELL, IF THEY DID NOTICE US,
THEN IT'S ALL OVER.
WHAT? IT'S OVER?
OVER FOR THEM,
NOT OVER FOR US!
OH, RIGHT, OVER FOR THEM!
SURE, I GET IT NOW.
YEAH, YOU'LL GET IT,
ALL RIGHT.
TERRIFIC! WAIT, ARE WE STILL
TALKING ABOUT THE SAME THING?
WELL, HELLO THERE,
EVERYBODY.
I BROUGHT YOU ALL SOME PB&J
WITH THE CRUST CUT OFF.
AW, YOU DIDN'T NEED
TO DO THAT.
All: THANKS, MRS. IZUMI!
THANKS, BUT YOU BETTER
GO HOME NOW.
CAN'T I STAY
FOR A WHILE?
BUT, MOM, THINGS MIGHT GET
REALLY UGLY.
OKAY, THEN,
I BETTER GO.
SO GO THEN!
OH!
PLEASE TRY TO UNDERSTAND
IZZY'S FEELINGS, MRS. IZUMI.
YOU'RE REALLY VERY IMPORTANT
TO HIM,
AND HE DOESN'T WANT ANYTHING
TO HAPPEN TO YOU.
I KNOW, IT'S JUST THAT...
THOSE CHILDREN --
I'M SURE THAT THEIR PARENTS
WOULD BE WORRIED ABOUT THEM
IF THEY KNEW
WHAT THEIR KIDS ARE DOING.
WAIT, THAT'S IT!
IF YOU DON'T NEED ME HERE,
I CAN GO TALK
TO THEIR PARENTS.
MAYBE I CAN GET THEIR FOLKS
TO COME DOWN HERE
AND SEE FOR THEMSELVES JUST
WHAT THEIR CHILDREN ARE DOING.
HEY, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA
THERE, MOM!
REALLY?
MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
OH, I'LL GO DO THAT
THEN.
GOODBYE, EVERYBODY.
BE CAREFUL!
All: BYE, MRS. IZUMI!
I DON'T KNOW IF BRINGING
THEIR PARENTS HERE
IS GOING TO HELP, THOUGH.
AND I DOUBT THAT EVEN
THEIR PARENTS WILL BE ABLE
TO REMOVE THE DARK SPORES
FROM INSIDE THEM.
T.K.: DON'T GIVE UP HOPE,
GUYS.
MAYBE THE PARENTS CAN REACH
THEIR KIDS IN A WAY
THAT WE CAN'T.
JUST THE WAY KARI WAS ABLE
TO REACH ME
WHEN I WAS WORKING
FOR MYOTISMON.
YEAH...
BUT...
THEY'RE RIGHT. I MEAN,
LOOK AT HOW YOU GUYS
WERE ABLE TO HELP
TURN ME AWAY FROM EVIL.
IF I CAN BE SAVED,
THEY CAN!
YEAH...
AND AS FOR THE PARENTS
TRYING TO HELP OUT,
THERE'S NO DOUBT IN MY MIND THAT
THEY WILL MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
YOU SEE, I BELIEVE THAT PART
OF THE REASON
THE DARK SPORES STOPPED GROWING
INSIDE OF ME
IS BECAUSE I WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO ACCEPT THE LOVE
MY PARENTS HAD BEEN TRYING
TO GIVE ME ALL THOSE YEARS.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ GIGGLES ]
EVERYONE,
SOMETHING IS HAPPENING!
All: HUH?
OWIKAWA!
LET'S GO GET
THAT CREEPY DUDE!
UHH!
WHAT?
RUN!
JUST WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
MOVE IT, LADY.
YOU'D BETTER NOT TOUCH
THOSE CHILDREN.
I'M AFRAID
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
YOU SEE, THE ROOTS
OF THE DARK FLOWERS
ARE SPREADING LIKE WILDFIRE,
AND IF THEY'RE NOT REMOVED
BEFORE THE GROWTH CYCLE
IS COMPLETE,
ALL OF THESE CHILDREN
WILL TURN INTO DARK TREES!
IS HE SERIOUS?
I'M NOT SURE. THAT'S NOT
WHAT HAPPENED WITH ME.
BUT CAN WE REALLY AFFORD
TO TAKE THE CHANCE?
YOUR SPORE WAS THE ORIGINAL,
SO IT WAS ABLE
TO LIVE INSIDE YOU
WITHOUT DESTROYING YOU,
BUT THE DARK SPORES
IN THESE CHILDREN
ARE ONLY COPIES OF YOURS,
SO THEY'RE IMPERFECT.
AND IT SEEMS THAT THEY'RE
COMPLETELY TAKING OVER.
HOW COULD YOU DO
SUCH A THING?
THEY WANTED THE SPORES.
ASK THEM.
Children: MM-HMM.
YOU'RE A LIAR!
AND NOW...
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
WE'RE ON OUR WAY
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
HEY, BANDAGE BRAIN,
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE DOING THAT
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO TELL THEM!
OH, RIGHT, I FORGOT.
LEAVE HIM ALONE,
ARUKENIMON.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
THAT THEY KNOW
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
THEY CAN DO TO STOP ME.
YEAH!
OH, YEAH?
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
NOW, REALLY.
I'VE SUCCESSFULLY SENT
ARUKENIMON AND MUMMYMON
FROM HERE TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
MANY TIMES BEFORE,
HAVEN'T I?
IT'S A WEAK SPOT
BETWEEN THE TWO WORLDS,
AND NOW THE DARK SPORES
WILL OPEN THE GATE!
BUT THAT'S THE GATE
THAT BLACK WARGREYMON --
SHH!
T.K.: BIGMOUTH!
WHEN THE GATE DOESN'T OPEN,
OWIKAWA WILL BE DISTRACTED,
AND THAT MAY GIVE US THE CHANCE
TO SAVE THOSE CHILDREN.
OH, I GOT YOU.
GOOD PLAN!
WELL, THIS IS
YOUR LAST CHANCE.
ANYTHING YOU'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO ASK ME?
WHY ME? WHY DID YOU
HAVE TO PICK ME?
OH, NOT THIS AGAIN!
I ALWAYS KNEW THAT YOU
WERE DIGIDESTINED...
AND I KNEW THAT YOU WERE
THE MOST VULNERABLE ONE --
OVERWHELMED
BY DARKNESS YOURSELF,
YOU WERE THE PERFECT TOOL.
BUT NOT FOREVER! WHAT ARE
THE DARK TOWERS?
A PRESENT FROM THE DARK OCEAN
TO KEEP YOU BUSY.
THEY PROVED TO BE
QUITE FORTUITOUS.
NOW, I SUPPOSE YOU WANT
TO KNOW THEIR PURPOSE.
WELL, THEY WERE
TO CHANGE THE BORDERS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
AND JUST WHAT DID YOU HOPE
TO ACCOMPLISH
BY CHANGING THE BORDERS?
IT'S SIMPLE, REALLY.
YOU SEE, I WANTED TO WEAKEN
THE DIGITAL WORLD'S DEFENSES.
BUT WHY WOULD YOU?
I COULD ALWAYS OPEN A GATE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT THERE WAS ONE LITTLE
PROBLEM --
ITS DEFENSES ALWAYS PREVENTED ME
FROM ENTERING.
SO I CREATED THESE TWO
BY TURNING MY DNA INTO DATA
AND SENT THEM INTO
THE DIGITAL WORLD IN MY PLACE.
BUT WHEN I SAW THEM THERE,
IT ONLY MADE ME
WANT TO GO MORE,
SO I USED YOU TO BUILD
THE CONTROL SPIRES, KEN.
BUT ALL YOU OTHER KIDS
RUINED THAT PLAN,
SO I HAD TO COME UP
WITH ANOTHER ONE.
IF I COULDN'T ALTER THE BARRIER
BETWEEN THE WORLDS
FROM INSIDE THE DIGITAL WORLD,
I'D DO IT
FROM INSIDE THE REAL ONE,
AND THAT'S WHEN I CAME UP WITH
THE IDEA FOR THE DARK SPORES,
EACH OF THEM FEEDING
ON THE INNOCENCE
THAT ENABLES A CHILD
TO ENTER THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND CONVERTING IT TO THE POWER
I NEEDED TO GO THERE MYSELF.
MY ONLY DREAM,
MY LIFELONG GOAL,
IS ALMOST WITHIN MY GRASP,
THANKS TO THESE
DELUDED CHILDREN.
I'VE WAITED SO LONG
FOR THIS!
[ SOBBING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
WHY IS HE CRYING?
HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
BOSS!
MY DREAM IS FINALLY
COMING TRUE!
OH, HIROKI, HOW I WISH
I COULD'VE BROUGHT YOU WITH ME!
[ ALL GASP ]
AND NOW, MY LITTLE CHILDREN,
ALL TOGETHER!
♪ BOYS AND GIRLS,
BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ LET'S GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
All: ♪ BOYS AND GIRLS,
BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
♪ LET'S GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD ♪
♪ BOYS AND GIRLS,
BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
HE'S TRYING
TO OPEN IT.
OKAY, GET READY
TO JUMP HIM!
HE'LL FIND OUT SOON ENOUGH
THAT "RING AROUND THE ROSY"
WON'T GET HIM
TO THE DIGIWORLD.
WE'RE READY!
Mummymon: THAT SONG
IS PRETTY CATCHY.
AHA, THIS IS IT!
HERE WE GO!
THE LONG WAIT IS OVER
AT LAST!
♪ BOYS AND GIRLS,
BOYS AND GIRLS ♪
AAH! IT OPENED!
YES, IT ACTUALLY WORKED!
CHILDREN, FOLLOW ME!
HEY, WHAT ABOUT US?
WAIT, DON'T LEAVE US
BEHIND!
WAIT UP!
HOW DID HE OPEN UP
THE GATE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO, GUYS?
SAVE THE WORLD,
AS USUAL! COME ON!
YEAH!
WAIT A MINUTE, YOU GUYS!
HOLD ON!
WE CAN'T JUST RUSH AFTER HIM!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
NO...
Izzy: WE'RE TOO LATE.
THEY'RE ALL ON THEIR OWN NOW.
Children: ♪ WE'RE HERE,
WE'RE HERE ♪
♪ THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS NEAR ♪
WE HAVE ARRIVED, CHILDREN.
WE ARE FINALLY HERE!
[ CHILDREN CHEERING ]
IT'S REAL.
I'VE SPENT SO MUCH TIME
DREAMING ABOUT THIS
THAT FINALLY BEING HERE
MAKES IT SEEM
AS IF I'VE ONLY FALLEN ASLEEP
AND RETURNED TO THAT DREAM,
BUT IT'S REAL.
THE DREAM IS REAL!
THE MOMENT I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR IS FINALLY HERE.
[ CHILD SCREAMS ]
[ OWIKAWA PANTING ]
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
WHY DON'T YOU PLAY
WITH THE OTHER CHILDREN?
THIS IS WRONG.
THIS IS JUST WRONG!
WE'RE NOT REALLY
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING? OF COURSE
IT'S THE DIGITAL WORLD.
NO, IT'S --
IT'S WRONG!
HUH? AAH!
WHA--
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
IF THIS ISN'T
THE DIGITAL WORLD,
THEN WHERE HAVE I
BROUGHT US?
Arukenimon: ACID MIST!
VEE-LASER!
LIGHTNING PAW!
THAT WAS JUST A SAMPLE
OF YOUR PARTING GIFTS!
YEAH, NOW LET
THOSE CHILDREN GO!
Owikawa: WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
IT'S GONE! WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO MY DREAM?
[ CRYING ]
HEY, WHERE ARE WE?
I DON'T KNOW.
BECAUSE BLACK WARGREYMON
SHUT THE DIGITAL GATE,
WE MUST'VE RICOCHETED
TO ANOTHER WORLD!
BUT WHICH WORLD THIS MIGHT BE,
I HAVE NO CLUE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THIS BEFORE!
[ GRUNTING ]
IT'S NOT FAIR! I WANTED TO GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD!
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS GET
WHAT YOU WANT, CAN YOU?
HUH?
THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A BIG MOUTH!
YOU CAN FORGET
THE DIGITAL WORLD, OWIKAWA.
IT IS BEYOND
YOUR REACH NOW.
YOU WILL NEVER SEE IT AGAIN,
EVEN IN YOUR DREAMS.
[ CHILDREN CRYING ]
YES, CRY.
YOU ARE DOOMED,
FOR YOU HAVE ENTERED
A WORLD OF DESPAIR
WHERE YOUR SOULS WILL BE
CONSUMED BY DARKNESS,
AND THERE IS NO PLACE
FOR YOU TO HIDE,
NOR HOPE FOR YOU TO ESCAPE.
[ CHILDREN SCREAMING ]
WHO OR WHAT ARE YOU?
ARE YOU WORKING WITH DAEMON
OR SOME OTHER WEIRDO?
DAEMON? HA!
AM I GOING CRAZY,
OR IS MY VOICE
COMING OUT OF THAT MOUTH?
A BIT OF BOTH, I THINK.
YOU SEE, I'M YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THREE YEARS AGO,
I WAS IN NEED OF A HOST,
AND WHEN I FOUND YOU,
I USED YOU TO STORE MY DATA.
THEN YOU AND I
BECAME AS ONE.
THREE YEARS AGO?
THAT WAS JUST ABOUT THE TIME
MY FRIEND HIROKI DIED.
HA HA HA HA!
YES, HIROKI --
THE FRIEND OVER WHOM
YOU PRETENDED TO GRIEVE,
BUT YOU SECRETLY HATED HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?
HATED HIM BECAUSE THE TWO OF YOU
HAD PROMISED TO GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD TOGETHER,
BUT HE LEFT YOU ALL ALONE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE! I COULD
NEVER HAVE HATED HIROKI.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
DO YOU NOT REMEMBER?
[ GASPS ]
LOOK -- HIROKI.
CAN YOU SEE IT?
IT'S THE DIGITAL WORLD WE WERE
SUPPOSED TO VISIT TOGETHER.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
CAN YOU SEE IT?
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO DO IT,
HIROKI?
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO DIE
AND LEAVE ME ALONE?
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?
LOOK -- THE DIGIDESTINED!
TAKE ME, TOO!
I WANT TO LEAVE THIS WORLD!
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD?
HMM?
WHAT'S THAT?
WHO'S THERE?
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
SOOTHE YOUR HEART WITH DARKNESS
AND I'LL TAKE YOU THERE.
YES, I'LL DO ANYTHING --
ANYTHING YOU WANT!
JUST TAKE ME THERE,
PLEASE!
SO BE IT.
[ GASPS ]
THAT WAS YOU?
THIS WHOLE TIME,
YOU'VE BEEN INSIDE OF ME,
CONTROLLING EVERYTHING
I DID?
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
I DO SO LOVE IRONY,
MY LITTLE MARIONETTE.
THAT VOICE!
WHAT?
I STILL HEAR THAT VOICE
IN MY NIGHTMARES.
MYOTISMON!
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
BUT HOW CAN THAT BE?
Kari: MYOTISMON?
Gatomon: YES!
I'M NOT SURPRISED
THAT YOU SAW THROUGH ME,
MY OLD PET,
BUT HERE'S SOMETHING
YOU DIDN'T KNOW --
THE DARK SPIRALS WERE BASED
ON YOUR OWN BELOVED TAIL RING,
SO IN A WAY, YOU CAUSED
THOSE DIGIMON TO BE ENSLAVED.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN THAT
ONLY YOUR TWISTED MIND
COULD COME UP WITH A PLAN
AS EVIL AS THIS!
IF IT TAKES MY NINE LIVES,
I'LL DESTROY YOU!
DELIGHTFUL.
BUT YOU'RE SO VERY MISGUIDED.
[ GROANING ]
AAH!
[ COUGHS ]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU SEEING DOUBLE?
OH, SORRY.
GATOMON GOT YOUR TONGUE?
OH, AND BY THE WAY,
ABOUT THE DARK SPORES
OPENING A DOORWAY
BETWEEN THE WORLDS --
THEY'RE REALLY JUST
THE BATTERIES
THAT WILL ALLOW ME
TO FINALLY BE REBORN.
YOU --
[ GROANS ]
[ CHILDREN BAWLING ]
PLEASE DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T DESTROY YOU YET.
I FIRST NEED TO HARVEST THE DARK
FLOWERS GROWING INSIDE OF YOU.
I WOULDN'T COUNT
ON THAT!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
FIGHT!
RIGHT!
OH, YEAH!
SPIDER THREAD!
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
THIS DARK FLOWER HAD ROAST BEEF,
THIS DARK FLOWER HAD NONE,
AND THIS DARK FLOWER CRIED,
"WEE, WEE, WEE --"
THAT'S REALLY GETTING
ON MY NERVES!
NOW, NOW,
LET HIM EAT IN PEACE.
AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST...
ALLOW ME TO REVEAL
MYSELF!
[ GROANING ]
YA!
LOOK, HE'S --
HE'S CHANGING!
BUT INTO MYOTISMON
OR VENOM MYOTISMON?
ACTUALLY...
YOU CAN CALL ME
MYELOMYOTISMON!
[ ALL GASP ]
FEAR ME.
HE'S NOTHING BUT A DEADLY
BLOOD-SUCKING FIEND.
NOTHING IS AS EVIL
AS MYELOMYOTISMON.
AAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'VE BEEN
YOUR FAITHFUL SERVANT, MASTER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'M DOING? TELL ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK YOU DO.
OOH! OOH!
SHOW ME
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
AAH!
ARUKENIMON!
All: OH!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
TO HER?
I JUST DID
WHAT SHE WAS THINKING.
NOW, REALLY,
IS THAT SO WRONG?
IS IT?
PLEASE STOP. JUST BECAUSE
I WAS THINKING IT,
DOESN'T MEAN
I REALLY WANT IT TO HAPPEN.
I LOVE THIS GAME.
SO, TELL ME,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'M GOING TO DO NEXT?
THINK HARD NOW.
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T WANT
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
BUT YOU ALREADY HAVE,
AND IT'S A TASTY IDEA.
UHH...
AAH!
ARUKENIMON!
All: OH!
DON'T HURT -- OH!
WHAT NEXT?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
SHOW ME WHAT YOU FEAR.
PLEASE.
NO, NOT THAT. OHH.
VERY WELL.
AAH!
OH! ARUKENIMON?
I'M AFRAID
SHE'S GONE TO PIECES.
ALL I DID WAS
GRANT HER HER WISH
TO GET AS FAR AWAY FROM ME
AS POSSIBLE
WHERE SHE'LL NEVER BE
NEAR ME AGAIN.
YOU DESTROYED HER.
HOW COULD YOU?
SNAKE BANDAGE!
UHH! YOU CAN'T HIDE
YOUR FEARS EITHER.
YOU THINK YOU DON'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST ME,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT. YOU DON'T.
YOU DON'T SCARE ME.
YOU'VE TAKEN AWAY
MY ARUKENIMON,
AND NOW I'M GOING
TO MAKE YOU PAY
FOR WHAT YOU DID TO HER!
HA! WHAT DO YOU
PLAN TO DO --
WRAP ME IN ANOTHER USELESS
SNAKE BANDAGE?
YOU SCARE ME EVEN LESS
THAN THESE DIGIDESTINED FOOLS
FROM THE OTHER WORLD.
THEN I WILL TEACH YOU
TO FEAR ME.
PLAY TIME IS OVER.
CRIMSON MIST!
UHH!
All: UHH!
KARI,
TIME TO DIGIVOLVE.
YOU CAN'T.
WHY NOT?
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO BE DESTROYED.
HUH?
COME ON, GUYS.
IT'S UP TO US TO STOP HIM.
I'VE NEVER FELT
LIKE THIS.
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO AFRAID
TO FIGHT BEFORE.
CAN'T SOMEONE ELSE FIGHT?
ANYONE ELSE. PLEASE?
THIS IS JUST A NIGHTMARE.
SOON I'LL WAKE UP.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU GUYS?
IF WE THINK WE CAN'T WIN,
THEN ALL OF US ARE DOOMED
FROM THE START.
WE'LL WIN, BUT WE'VE GOT TO
BELIEVE IN OURSELVES.
HE'S RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY.
HUH?
I'LL FIGHT HIM
ALL BY MYSELF, DAVIS.
WHAT?
BUT YOU CAN'T FIGHT ALONE.
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
YOU THINK I'M GOING TO LOSE,
DON'T YOU?
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE.
BELIEVE IN ME.
YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE
THAT WE CAN DEFEAT HIM.
[ GROANING ]
RIGHT! LET'S FIGHT!
JUST IMAGINE
IT'S THE LAST MINUTE
OF A SOCCER GAME.
IT'S YOU AGAINST THE GOALIE.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO, RIGHT?
NOT A CLUE.
BEAT THE BAD GUY.
RIGHT.
YOU DON'T LOOK SO TOUGH.
KEN, PLEASE.
WAIT -- MYELOMYOTISMON
IS TOO POWERFUL
FOR XV-MON ALONE.
WE NEED TO DNA DIGIVOLVE,
RIGHT?
YOUR HAND --
IT'S SHAKING.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I'M AFRAID.
HEY, WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO DNA DIGIVOLVE
IF YOU'RE AFRAID OF IT,
KEN.
NOW I'VE GOT A BAD GUY
TO BEAT.
I, UH, UH...
NOW DON'T SAY
ANOTHER WORD, KEN.
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE AFRAID,
BUT YOU CAN'T GIVE IN TO IT.
YOU CAN'T LET FEAR
CONTROL YOU.
UHH...
WE'VE TO HIDE OUR FEARS
FROM MYELOMYOTISMON
OR HE'LL USE THEM
AGAINST US.
WE'VE GOT TO.
LET'S GET HIM,
XV-MON.
YOU WILL WIN.
YOU MUST DEFEAT HIM.
[ GROWLING ]
CAN THE DIGIDESTINED OVERCOME
THEIR FEAR
AND BAND TOGETHER TO DEFEAT
THE EVIL MYELOMYOTISMON?
KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"
TO FIND OUT.