DAVIS:
Arukenimon had us
caught in her
web of evil, literally.
Our Digimon were under
the spell of her magic flute,
and she had them
fighting each other.
Meanwhile, T. K., Kari
and Yolei were fighting off
her insect
Digimon creatures.
Cody helped us escape,
and then we distorted
the flute to help the others.
That finally broke the spell
and we were able to face
Arukenimon head to head.
Of course we didn't realize
she had a spider's head.
She was actually an
Ultimate Digimon.
With the help of Paildramon
we managed to capture her,
but Mummymon put the wraps
on us and they escaped.
♪ Di di di ♪
♪ Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Change into
digital champions ♪
♪ To save
the digital world ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
Digivolve into champions.
Armor
Digivolve!
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon ♪
ARUKENIMON:
Those Digibrats make me
so tense.
I've got to try and relax.
Maybe I should think
happy thoughts.
Let's see, evil spells,
crushing my enemies,
more Control Spires,
less DigiDestined.
Oh, I can't keep those
kids out of my head.
How hard can it be
to get rid of them?
Where did I go wrong?
(Arukenimon grunts)
MUMMYMON:
Oh, there you are.
Usually a bubble bath
relaxes me
but not this time.
(groaning)
MUMMYMON:
Arukenimon, a rather unusual
place for a tub,
don't you think?
Well, I guess
all you have to do
is build the rest
of the house around it.
(laughs)
Let's do it!
Let's go get 'em!
(T. K. yells)
You're next!
PAILDRAMON:
Desperado Blaster!
♪ Hello! ♪
That sure
does look comfortable.
I haven't had a bath
like that in years.
Do you think that I could‐‐
Would you be quiet?
Can't you see I'm
trying to concentrate?
Those kids are destroying
my supply of Control Spires.
I'll just have
to work faster.
(laughs)
MUMMYMON:
In the meantime,
mind if I take a dip?
FLAMEDRAMON:
Fire Rocket!
(fire roaring)
(spire rumbling)
Way to go!
SHURIMON:
Double Stars!
(spire rumbling)
Awesome!
DIGMON:
Rock Cracking!
(ground cracking)
Digmon, nice job!
PEGASUSMON:
Shooting Star!
(spire rumbling)
That a boy!
NEFERTIMON:
Rosetta Star!
(spire rumbling)
Say cheese, please.
STINGMON:
Spiking Strike!
(spire rumbling)
KEN:
I can't believe it.
We're actually
making progress.
That's 147 so far today.
I think we can all
use a break.
Let's eat.
Yeah!
KARI:
I'm thirsty.
Me too.
T. K.:
There was a vending machine
with juice in it
back there a ways.
Well then,
why are we here?
Hopefully it has milk,
preferably in a saucer.
Count me in.
Me too, I'm coming.
Don't worry, we'll
just get something
and bring it back
to you, okay?
Huh?
(groans)
Hey, what kind
should we get you?
Whatever.
Davis, what's
the matter with you?
(groans)
Nothing.
VEEMON:
I know when something's wrong,
and something's wrong.
Now what's wrong?
DAVID:
Stop asking me what's wrong!
Huh?
Hey Davis, what's wrong?
Hi, Yolei.
Are you just gonna
stay up there
and be crabby all day?
Look, I'm not crabby,
get it through your
thick head.
Ah, now there's
the old Davis.
Why don't you come down
here and we'll talk?
Huh?
YOLEI:
It's about Cody and Ken.
Have you noticed they
never talk to each other?
They're not friends.
And it's not like they
argue the way you and I do.
They just don't talk.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess they're still
both a little nervous
around each other.
Well, they can't go on
like this much longer.
Well, what are we
suppose to do about it?
Actually, I've got a plan.
Listen.
It's worth a shot.
Hey Ken, Cody,
I need a hand.
BOTH: Huh?
See that Control Spire
over there?
It's right behind you.
It's seems that Flamedramon
wasn't strong enough
to knock that one down.
Are you nuts?
I can do that
blindfolded!
‐ (Veemon grunting)
‐ YOLEI: Quiet!
It's a plan to get Cody
and Ken to work together.
VEEMON:
Oh! Nevermind.
It's really kinda strange.
Yeah, go figure,
you know?
(nervous laughing)
(Digimon stomping)
STINGMON:
Spiking Strike!
DIGMON:
Rock Cracking!
(spire rumbling)
BOTH:
Yay! We did it!
Wormmon and Armadillomon
seem to be
getting along just fine.
(monsters giggling)
Yeah, now if only
Cody and Ken
would act the same way.
That's enough!
You two just worked
together
to destroy
a Control Spire,
why don't you shake hands
and be friends?
CODY: Davis!
What?
I think Flamedramon
could have destroyed
that Control Spire.
I agree with Cody.
Well, now that you
mention it‐‐
Davis, please don't make us
waste our energy
like that again.
Cody, you're so stubborn!
Yolei, stop,
you're not helping.
It seems not every
team member
wants us around Wormmon.
Let's go.
‐ BOTH: But wait!
‐ Ken!
ARMADILLOMON:
Wormmon, where ya going?
(groans)
You!
Cody.
I'm going to need an
all powerful Digimon
if I ever hope to squeeze
the life out
of the DigiDestined.
When I only used
one Control Spire‐‐
(spire humming)
This is what I created.
And then I tried using
10 Control Spires.
Spirit Needle!
And I created this
powerful creature.
And yet neither of them
was sufficient enough
to defeat those kids.
In order to destroy those kids
I'll need to use
100 Control Spires.
MUMMYMON:
If she's going
to use 100 Control Spires
how many hairs
does she need?
Let's see, that's six,
carry the four, minus two,
that would be a hundred.
If you have to use
a hundred hairs
you could get a job
in the circus
as the bald lady.
(laughs)
ARUKENIMON:
And you can join the circus
on the flying trapeze.
(Mummymon yells)
(trees rustling)
(Arukenimon laughs)
MUMMYMON:
Every time she treats me
like that
I feel closer,
and closer to her.
Could this be love
I'm feeling?
(engine revving)
ARUKENIMON: Mummymon!
Would you hurry it up?
We're leaving.
MUMMYMON: I'm coming!
(engine revving)
♪ 99 Control Spires on
the side of the road ♪
♪ 99 Control Spires ♪
♪ You knock one down ♪
ARUKENIMON: Oh, be quiet!
Look at all those
beautiful Control Spires.
I need those eager‐beaver
brats didn't have time
to clean up
this area yet.
Are you ready?
(laughs)
MUMMYMON:
I love watching you work.
Then you're really
gonna love this.
This creature will not only
destroy the DigiDestined,
but also the entire
Digital World.
Digimon of darkness,
come to me!
(light orchestral music)
(sighing)
DAVIS:
And that's the whole story.
He's been up there
ever since.
We're gone 10 minutes
and you cause a mutiny?
Both of them are
so stubborn,
neither one of them
is willing to talk to the other.
I feel sorry for Cody.
I'm sure he feels terrible.
(all sighing)
(juice gurgling)
You know what?
I was thinking,
maybe I should talk
to both of them
about acting their own age.
(choking)
I think I can
straighten them out.
(all laughing)
Alright, what
exactly is so funny?
ALL: Huh?
(dramatic orchestral music)
Uh, look,
are you guys mad?
(tires screeching)
You don't have to give
me the silent treatment.
I mean, come on!
Davis, take a look behind you.
Huh?
(maniacal laughing)
Shouldn't you
boys and girls
be home with your
mommies and daddies?
None of your business!
Alright,
what do you want?
I thought you kids
might enjoy
playing with a little
Digimon I put together.
When will you learn?
Every time you try
to fight us,
you end up losing.
Not this time.
Spirit
Needle!
(spires pulsating)
(gasps)
(tires screeching)
Have a good time.
Play nice.
(spires squealing)
(ground rumbling)
Davis!
Right!
DIGITAL VOICE:
Digimon.
VEEMON:
Veemon digivolve to
EXVEEMON: ExVeemon.
♪ Digimon ♪
Digi‐Armor energize!
♪ Digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
PATAMON:
Patamon Armor digivolve to
(dramatic electronic music)
PEGASUSMON: Pegasusmon,
Flying Hope!
DIGITAL VOICE:
Digimon.
HAWKMON:
Hawkmon digivolve to
AQUILAMON: Aquilamon!
♪ Digimon ♪
DIGITAL VOICE:
Digimon
ARMADILLOMON:
Armadillomon digivolve to
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
ANKYLOMON: Ankylomon!
♪ Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon ♪
(spires exploding)
DIGITAL VOICE:
Digimon.
Digi‐Armor energize!
♪ Digimon ♪
♪ Digital Monsters ♪
GATOMON:
Gatomon armor digivolve to
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
Armor!
Digivolve!
NEFERTIMON:
Nefertimon, the Angel of Life!
♪ Digimon ♪
Let's do it!
Now that's funny.
They think they have
a chance.
(dramatic orchestral music)
This is fun.
Nothing quite relaxes
me like scaring kids.
Come on guys, hurry.
I've got a bad feeling
about this.
T. K. and Kari are
too far ahead.
KARI:
T. K., what's that?
(air blasting)
(Kari screams)
‐ Ugh!
‐ Kari!
T. K.!
(crashing and groaning)
(dramatic orchestral music)
PEGASUSMON:
I know who that is.
NEFERTIMON:
It's BlackWarGreymon.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(yelling mightily)
DIGIVICE:
BlackWarGreymon is
a Mega‐Digimon who looks
like WarGreymon
but he's pure evil.
His Terra Destroyer attack
releases a concentration
of 100% negative energy.
BlackWarGreymon?
It can't be.
It is.
But I don't know
how it's possible.
What should we do Ankylomon?
I'd say protecting
the kids is high on the list.
I agree, wholeheartedly.
(growling)
(claw scraping)
(ExVeemon groaning)
(ground rumbles)
(Digimon thuds)
(both laughing)
(fists thudding)
(monsters grunting)
He's too strong for them!
They need more help, now!
Paildramon is
the only one who
is strong enough
to help.
That's it then,
we have to call Ken.
(Digivice beeping)
STINGMON:
Finally, I'm good at something.
KEN: Email.
It's from Yolei.
STINGMON:
What does she want, Ken?
YOLEI:
I don't want to mess up
the dynamics of your team.
Worrying about our team
is the least
of our problems.
CODY:
I say forget about Ken.
We never needed him before,
and we don't need him now.
We can do this on
our own.
You're wrong.
Both of you,
knock it off.
You're acting like
a couple of 12 year olds.
You know what I mean.
Aquilamon!
You called?
We're gonna find Ken
and bring him back.
Hold the fort until then.
Right!
(BlackWarGreymon growling)
I have created
a magnificent specimen.
If I do say so myself.
(Ankylomon groaning)
(BlackWarGreymon growling)
‐ Ken?
‐ Huh?
Are you sure
you don't want to go?
Go where?
You know where.
Davis and the others
called you, didn't they?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Hey, Ken, it's me!
Huh? Yolei?
What are you doing here?
You have to hurry.
Arukenimon made this
really strong Digimon,
we need Paildramon.
STINGMON: Ken!
Yolei, I can't go.
You must!
I'm sorry.
Why you!
(screams)
(hand slaps)
KARI:
It's Ken and Yolei.
I'm sorry
I slapped you,
but you needed
to wake up.
(Ken groans)
(ExVeemon groans)
(ground shakes)
(BlackWarGreymon snarling)
Let's keep fighting.
I'm sure that Stingmon
will show up soon.
Right.
BlackWarGreymon,
it's time!
Finish them off
once and for all.
(monsters growling)
Arukenimon is your master.
You must do what
she tells you.
Davis, I brought Stingmon
and Ken to give us a hand.
Alright!
Let's get to work.
DIGITAL VOICE:
Digimon.
ExVeemon.
Stingmon
BOTH:
DNA Digivolve to
Paildramon!
♪ Digimon ♪
♪ Digital Monsters ♪
(Paildramon growling)
BlackWarGreymon,
I've seen this
mutant Digimon before.
I want you to show him
who's the most powerful
Digimon in the entire
Digital World.
(BlackWarGreymon growls)
This is gonna get ugly.
(crashing)
(grunting)
Wow, talk about
meeting head to head.
We're gonna need
an aspirin the size
of a Control Spire
after this fight.
Desperado Blaster!
(lasers firing)
(rocks rumbling)
Uh‐oh.
(laughing maniacally)
Look, there's not even
a scratch on him.
Impossible.
DAVIS:
Paildramon was our only chance.
Now what do we do?
(Arukenimon chuckles)
(gasping)
Let's get out of here!
(explosion thundering)
(DigiDestined groaning)
(BlackWarGreymon stomps)
(growling)
You have done an outstanding
job, BlackWarGreymon.
You may now proceed
to destroy the Digital World.
MUMMYMON:
Don't just stand there,
patting yourself
on the back,
your master has
given you new orders.
Now get to work!
BLACKWARGREYMON:
I will take orders from no one.
BOTH: You what?
BLACKWARGREYMON:
Why should I take orders
from you when you're so
weak you need me
to do your fighting
for you?
I must find a more
worthy opponent.
(loud soaring)
(Arukenimon groans)
MUMMYMON: Arukenimon!
Can you hear me?
Speak to me, my darling.
(Arukenimon grumbles)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(Arukenimon groans)
NARRATOR:
How can the DigiDestined
handle BlackWarGreymon
and Arukenimon
at the same time?
Find out on the next
Digimon: Digital Monsters.
(children laughing)
(Digimon theme song)