Girl:
MUSHROOMON AND FLORAMON
HAD BECOME SLAVES
OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
AND THEY ATTACKED US.
NINJAMON GOT INTO A BATTLE
WITH SHURIMON.
GEKOMON WAS THERE
TO HELP US,
AND WE HID IN THE UNDERGROUND
CASTLE OF SHOGUNGEKOMON.
NINJAMON SECRETLY SLIPPED IN
AND PUT A DARK SPIRAL
ON SHOGUNGEKOMON
WHILE HE WAS SLEEPING.
HE WENT BERSERK!
WE COULDN'T CONTROL HIM,
SO WE TRICKED HIM
INTO DESTROYING THE DARK TOWER
AND THEN PUT HIM
BACK TO SLEEP.
WORKING TOGETHER,
WE REMOVED THE DARK SPIRAL
AND RETURNED HOME.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ GROWLING ]
MEGASEADRAMON
IS STILL OUT THERE.
WHY DOESN'T HE
ATTACK US?
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO
BECAUSE HE KNOWS
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE OUR AIR SUPPLY
RUNS OUT DOWN HERE.
[ SOBBING ]
I'M AFRAID OF BEING DOWN HERE
IN THE OCEAN.
[ Thinking ]
I'D GIVE ANYTHING
TO BE OUT
IN THE FRESH AIR AGAIN.
WE WERE ALL FINE
A LITTLE WHILE AGO
WHEN WE WERE TRACKING
THE SIGNAL OF A NEW DIGIEGG.
OKAY, THIS IS IT.
THIS IS A STRANGE PLACE
TO FIND A DIGIEGG, DAVIS.
IF THE DIGIVICE SAYS IT'S UNDER
AN OFFSHORE OIL PLATFORM,
WHO AM I TO ARGUE?
WHERE IS THE DIGIEGG?
ACCORDING TO THE D-3,
WE'RE ON TOP OF IT.
YOU MEAN IN THE WATER?
HOPE IT'S WATERPROOF.
I'M JUST WONDERING
IF THE EGG BELONGS TO T.K.
OR KARI OR MAYBE --
HEY, WAIT!
I'M GOING TO GO LOOK
FOR THAT DIGIEGG.
LAST ONE THERE
IS A ROTTEN DIGIEGG.
WE SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
All: HEY, WAIT UP!
[ ROARS ]
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
TO THOSE KIDS, MASTER?
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THEM.
I'M TAKING OVER THE WORLD
AT NOON,
AND THEN
I HAVE A LUNCH DATE.
MEGASEADRAMON,
YOU HAVE MY PERMISSION
TO DO WITH THEM
WHAT YOU WILL.
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
LIGHTNING JAVELIN!
THIS IS REALLY GOING TO
HIKE UP OIL PRICES!
I'VE HEARD
OF EARTHQUAKES BEFORE,
BUT NEVER OCEAN QUAKES.
WHOA.
THE ROOM IS FLOODING!
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
DAVIS, LOOK, I FOUND
AN EMERGENCY SHUT-OFF VALVE!
I'D CLASSIFY THIS
AS AN EMERGENCY,
SO WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
HIT THE SWITCH!
GREAT. THE WATER
CAN'T GET IN.
YEAH,
BUT WE CAN'T GET OUT.
EVEN IF WE COULD,
WE'D JUST BE BAIT
BECAUSE MEGASEADRAMON'S
OUT THERE WAITING FOR US.
HA HA HA!
[ Thinking ]
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO SCARED
IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE IT
OUT ALIVE, ARE WE?
WHY ARE YOU SO UPSET?
I'VE HAD THIS NIGHTMARE
EVER SINCE I WAS LITTLE --
I WAS TRAPPED
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN
AND I COULDN'T GET OUT.
HEY, WE'LL FIND A WAY
OUT OF HERE.
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
BY THE WAY,
HOW DID IT END?
I ALWAYS WOKE UP.
WELL, THIS DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A DREAM.
IT SURE LOOKS REAL TO ME.
WHAT IS IT?
I DO BELIEVE IT SAYS
IT'S AN EMERGENCY
EJECTION VEHICLE.
Davis:
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE SAVED!
LOOK OUT, SUNSHINE,
HERE WE COME.
UH-OH. IT ONLY HOLDS
ONE PERSON.
IN THAT CASE,
CODY SHOULD BE THE ONE TO GO.
HE'S THE ONE.
I AGREE.
I THINK WE ALL AGREE,
RIGHT, DAVIS?
HUH?
WELL, HOW ABOUT IT?
YEAH?
OF COURSE I AGREE.
CODY'S THE ONE TO GO.
THEN IT'S ALL SETTLED.
GO AHEAD, CODY.
CLIMB INTO THE POD.
THE REASON YOU WANT ME TO GO
IS BECAUSE I'M AFRAID.
I WON'T GO.
I HAVE TO FACE MY FEAR.
YOU'RE GOING TO
GET OUT OF HERE ALIVE.
I'D BE ALL OVER IT
LIKE A CHEAP SUIT.
ALL RIGHT, THEN YOU GO.
I CAN'T GO
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING!
I AM NOT GOING!
I CAN'T TELL WHICH ONE
OF THEM IS THE YOUNGEST.
RELAX. I'VE GOT A PLAN.
WE'LL DRAW STRAWS,
AND WHOEVER WINS GETS TO GO.
IT SOUNDS FAIR TO ME.
NOT ME. I'M NOT GOOD
AT DRAWING.
THAT SEEMS LIKE
A REALLY GOOD PLAN, YOLEI.
I'M IN. HOW DOES THAT
SOUND TO YOU, CODY?
UH, MM-HMM.
DON'T BOTHER MAKING
ANY STRAWS FOR ME, YOLEI.
I'M NOT THIRSTY.
THEY SHOULD MAKE STRAWS
FOR ALL OF US.
I AGREE.
WE SHOULD ALL HAVE
AN EQUAL CHANCE
TO MAKE IT OUT OF HERE.
RIGHT, ONE FOR ALL
AND ALL FOR ME!
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S HOW IT GOES.
Yolei: ONE OF THEM
HAS RED ON THE BOTTOM.
OKAY.
WAIT. LET'S LET CODY
GO FIRST.
BUT WHY ME?
JUST DO IT, CODY.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
CODY, YOU'RE IT!
YOU PICKED THE STRAW
ON THE FIRST TRY.
TALK ABOUT BEGINNER'S LUCK.
THAT WAS AMAZING, CODY.
SO CLIMB IN.
HEY, WHAT DID YOU
DO THAT FOR?
ALL THE STRAWS
HAVE RED ON THEM.
THE FIRST ONE
WAS SO PRETTY,
I JUST COULDN'T
STOP COLORING?
YOU CHEATED!
WE HAD
NO OTHER CHOICE.
YOU WERE BEING
SO STUBBORN ABOUT IT.
I GUESS THEY SET
THE WHOLE THING UP
SO CODY WOULD FEEL
LIKE HE HAD TO GO.
NEITHER OF YOU TWO
WERE IN ON THE PLAN?
YOU MEAN
EVERYONE KNEW BUT US?
Yolei: OF COURSE WE DID.
SO WHAT?
I'M STILL NOT GOING.
Yolei: DAVIS, T.J.
RIGHT.
HEY, LET ME GO!
PUT ME DOWN!
Davis: NOW, CODY,
MAKE SURE YOU KEEP
YOUR ARMS AND LEGS
INSIDE THE RIDE
AT ALL TIMES.
FIND JOE AND TELL HIM
WHAT HAPPENED.
IKKAKUMON'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN GET US OUT
OF THIS PLACE.
GOOD LUCK, CODY.
WAIT A SECOND, GUYS!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
[ ROARS ]
OKAY, MEGASEADRAMON'S
NOT WATCHING.
LET'S DO IT.
RIGHT.
[ Thinking ]
OKAY, I CAN DO THIS
IF I JUST HOLD
PERFECTLY STILL.
I MADE IT!
OH, FRESH AIR.
Hi, this is Joe.
Sorry I can't answer
my cell phone right now,
but I had to turn it off
so it wouldn't ring
during my biology test.
I'm pretty good at biology,
so I'll turn it back on
real soon,
unless the test
is on molecular biology.
I have to go study. Bye.
[ Thinking ]
I HAVE TO FIND JOE'S SCHOOL.
OH, CODY, YOU'RE HOME.
I'M GLAD BECAUSE
I HAVE SOME ERRANDS
I WANT YOU TO RUN FOR ME.
DO YOU WANT TO
WRITE IT DOWN?
I CAN'T.
I'M KIND OF BUSY.
WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT?
COME ON, CODY.
YOU CAN TELL ME WHAT IT IS.
I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T.
I DON'T LIKE YOU
KEEPING SECRETS FROM ME.
YOU SHOULD NOT KEEP
ASKING HIM ABOUT IT.
IF HE'S FORCED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING,
HE MIGHT HAVE TO
TELL YOU A LIE,
EVEN THOUGH THAT'S NOT
WHAT HE WANTS TO DO.
IT'S BETTER THAT HE SAY
NOTHING AT ALL
RATHER THAN SAY SOMETHING
THAT ISN'T THE TRUTH.
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE
THAN TELLING A LIE, YOU SEE?
PRUNE JUICE SURE
MAKES YOU SMART, GRANDPA.
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
THANKS, GRANDPA.
Yolei: DO YOU HAVE TO
KEEP BANGING YOUR HEAD?
YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY!
IT HURTS JUST WATCHING YOU.
I'LL STOP WHEN YOU STOP
TAPPING YOUR FOOT LIKE THAT.
IT'S RATHER ANNOYING!
HOW ABOUT IF I TAP MY FOOT
ON YOUR HEAD?
THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU TWO
TO BE FIGHTING...
WE'RE NOT!
OR ARGUING.
GOOD. WELL,
I'M GLAD THAT'S SETTLED.
NOW, HOW ABOUT
A NICE GAME OF CHECKERS?
WE COULD USE MY SHELL
AS THE BOARD.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE
PLAYING A GAME RIGHT NOW.
HOW CAN YOU BE THINKING
OF PLAYING GAMES
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
EASY, 'CAUSE I KNOW CODY
WILL COME AND RESCUE US.
WE ALL KNOW CODY
WILL TRY HIS BEST,
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW
IF HE'LL MAKE IT BACK
IN TIME.
MY GUESS
IS THAT WE'VE ONLY GOT
A COUPLE OF HOURS LEFT.
SHORTLY AFTER THAT,
WE'LL COMPLETELY
RUN OUT OF AIR.
HUH?
I'M SORRY, BUT HE'S
TAKING A TEST RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
I NEED TO SEE JOE.
THE RULES SAY
DON'T INTERRUPT ANYONE
DURING THE TEST.
IF THERE HAD BEEN
SOME KIND OF ACCIDENT
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
IT WOULD BE
A DIFFERENT STORY.
OTHERWISE,
YOU HAVE TO WAIT.
BUT THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT...
AND SOMEONE MIGHT HAVE TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE
THAN LYING. UNDERSTAND?
YEAH, BUT WHAT DO I DO NOW?
Yolei: T.K., WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OVER THERE?
I THINK THE DIGIEGG
IS BURIED SOMEWHERE IN HERE,
SO I'M TRYING TO FIND IT.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
MORE WORRIED
ABOUT TRYING
TO GET OUT OF HERE?
I JUST DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE SITTING AROUND HERE
DOING NOTHING,
SO I FIGURED AT LEAST
LET'S FIND THE DIGIEGG.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
LET'S HELP.
RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SHALL WE?
SURE.
YEAH, LET'S.
MY DAD'S IN THE HOSPITAL?
HOLD ON, PA!
SORRY I LIED
BUT I HAD TO GET YOU
OUT OF CLASS.
I'M JUST GLAD TO KNOW
MY DAD'S OKAY.
BESIDES, THIS IS
A REAL EMERGENCY
AND YOU HAD
NO OTHER CHOICE.
SINCE YOUR DAD'S ALL RIGHT,
WHY ARE YOU STILL RUNNING?
RIGHT, YEAH.
I'VE GOT TO TURN
MY PHONE BACK ON.
NOW?
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
I'VE GOT TO TELL IZZY.
FOR ONCE IN YOUR LIFE,
GET OFF THE COMPUTER
AND ANSWER THE PHONE.
THE OTHERS ARE TRAPPED UNDER
AN OFFSHORE OIL PLATFORM
AND THEY NEED OUR HELP.
I WANT YOU TO TRACK DOWN
AN OLD FRIEND OF OURS.
[ ALL GASPING ]
I GUESS IT'S NOT MINE.
THEN THAT MUST MEAN
IT BELONGS TO CODY.
YEAH, AND THAT MEANS
THAT I'M THE ONE
WHO GETS TO ARMOR DIGIVOLVE.
I WONDER WHAT KIND OF DIGIMON
YOU'RE GOING TO BE.
I THINK I HAVE
A PRETTY GOOD IDEA --
LIKE THIS.
I THINK IT'LL BE
MORE LIKE THIS,
KIND OF LIKE A PORCUPINE.
I KIND OF HOPE
HE'S THE HANDSOME ONE.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
I DON'T GET IT. HOW COME
EVERYONE'S LAUGHING?
IT'S JUST ONE OF THOSE TIMES
WHEN YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT LAUGH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SEE, EVERYONE'S SO TIRED,
THEY'RE PRETENDING
NOTHING'S WRONG.
LAUGHTER'S JUST A WAY
TO COVER THINGS UP.
YOU KNOW, SORT OF LIKE I DO
IN THE CAT BOX.
HOW SAD.
[ COUGHS ]
YOLEI, ARE YOU GOING TO
BE ALL RIGHT?
I THINK SO.
AM I SEEING THINGS?
IKKAKUMON.
[ GASPS ]
LOOK, EVERYBODY!
IKKAKUMON'S HERE
TO SAVE US!
[ ALL GASP ]
Both: IKKAKUMON!
SORRY I'M LATE.
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
IT'S MEGASEADRAMON,
MY OLD FOE.
HE'S AN ULTIMATE-LEVEL
DIGIMON
WHO DESTROYS HIS ENEMIES
WITH HIS LIGHTNING JAVELIN
AND MEGA-ICE BLAST ATTACKS.
I FACED HIM ONCE BEFORE
IN TOKYO,
BUT I DON'T THINK
I CAN DEFEAT HIM
UNLESS I DIGIVOLVE
TO ZUDOMON.
AAH!
IKKAKUMON!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
THAT'S THE WAY!
KEEP GOING!
AIM FOR THE DARK SPIRAL!
HARPOON TORPEDO!
LIGHTNING JAVELIN!
AAH!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
OH, GREAT.
NOW WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Joe: WHAMON'S TAXI SERVICE.
COME ON, IT'LL BE
THE PERFECT WAY OUT OF HERE
EXCEPT FOR THE SMELL.
LOOK, IT'S CODY, JOE!
I TOLD YOU CODY WOULD COME
THROUGH FOR US, DIDN'T I?
YOU SURE DID,
AND WE NEVER DOUBTED HIM.
I DON'T GET IT.
HOW'D YOU GET HERE?
WHEN TENTOMON TOLD ME
OUR FRIENDS WERE IN TROUBLE,
I SET SAIL.
HAVE YOU LOST WEIGHT?
A COUPLE POUNDS.
HEY, CODY!
WHAT?
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT'S YOUR DIGIEGG.
IT IS?
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
THAT DIGIEGG HAS THE CREST
OF RELIABILITY ON IT.
THE CREST OF RELIABILITY
IS PERFECT FOR CODY.
I DON'T AGREE WITH THAT.
WELL, IF YOU ASK ME,
I THINK IT'S A PERFECT FIT.
COME DOWN AND GET IT!
NO WAY. IT'S BECAUSE
OF THAT DIGIEGG
THAT ALL OF US
WERE TRAPPED DOWN HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
[ COUGHS ]
BESIDES,
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
WE HAVE TO GO.
AS SOON AS YOU COME DOWN
AND GET THIS DIGIEGG.
I TOLD YOU THAT
I DON'T WANT IT!
LISTEN, WE DIDN'T
GO THROUGH ALL OF THIS
JUST SO YOU CAN SAY THANKS,
BUT NO THANKS.
Joe: CODY, COME WITH ME.
ALL RIGHT, CODY,
PICK IT UP.
IT'S ALL YOURS.
YOU HEARD WHAT JOE SAID.
IT CAN'T BE MINE.
THERE'S NO WAY.
YOU'LL NEVER KNOW
UNLESS YOU TRY,
SO GO AHEAD.
I'M THE ONE
WHO CAUSED THIS MESS,
SO IT CAN'T BE MY DIGIEGG.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
WE ALL WANTED TO FIND
THE DIGIEGG, NOT JUST YOU.
SO IT'S NOBODY'S
FAULT, THEN.
YEAH, BUT I ALSO TOLD A LIE.
MY GRANDFATHER SAID
THE WORSE THING YOU COULD DO
IS TELL A LIE,
AND THAT'S JUST WHAT I DID.
I DON'T DESERVE THE DIGIEGG
OF RELIABILITY.
THERE'S TWO KINDS
OF LIES, CODY --
THERE ARE LIES THAT ARE WRONG
AND THEN THERE ARE THE LIES
THAT ARE ACCEPTABLE.
SOME LIES CAN HURT PEOPLE.
THEN AGAIN, SOME CAN
ACTUALLY HELP THEM.
JUST LIKE THERE'S GOOD DIGIMON
AND BAD DIGIMON.
YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WHEN WE GET BACK,
I'LL EXPLAIN THE SITUATION
TO YOUR GRANDFATHER.
I'LL TELL HIM I WASN'T HURT
BY YOUR LIE.
IF YOU DIDN'T LIE,
WE MIGHT NOT HAVE
MADE IT IN TIME.
YOUR LIE
NOT ONLY HELPED PEOPLE,
BUT ACTUALLY
SAVED THEIR LIVES.
SO, DO WE HAVE A DEAL?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, CODY,
GO FOR IT.
Davis: SEE, I TOLD YOU
IT WAS YOURS.
PARTNER, I'M READY
WHEN YOU ARE.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
SUBMARIMON,
GUARDIAN OF THE SEAS.
Davis: SO MUCH FOR MY IDEA
OF THE PORCUPINE.
WOW. A SUBMARINE --
WHAT PERFECT TIMING.
I AM SUBMARIMON.
I DIGIVOLVE USING THE DIGIEGG
OF RELIABILITY.
MY OXYGEN TORPEDO ATTACK
MAKES MY ENEMIES
TRULY SEASICK.
Joe: ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
COME ON, CODY. HOP IN.
I HAVE TO FACE THIS
SOONER OR LATER.
SUBMARINE ATTACK!
IKKAKUMON,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, NOW LET'S TAKE CARE
OF THIS WORM TOGETHER.
♪ IT'S GETTING STRANGER
AND THEN ♪
LIGHTNING JAVELIN!
♪ IT'S GETTING DIGITAL NOW ♪
I'LL GET HIM TO FOLLOW ME.
YOU SNEAK UP ON HIM.
GOT IT!
♪ HEY, IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT AS WELL BE
A SUPERSTAR ♪
I'M UP HERE,
YOU OVERGROWN GARDEN SNAKE!
AAH!
OXYGEN TORPEDO!
♪ IT'S GETTING STRANGER
AND THEN ♪
♪ IT'S GETTING HARDER
TO WIN ♪
NOW FOR THE DARK SPIRAL.
♪ IT STARTS HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN ♪
WAY TO GO!
YOU DID IT!
WELL, HE SHOULD BE BACK
TO NORMAL NOW.
NICE JOB, SUBMARIMON.
THANKS. COULDN'T HAVE
DONE IT WITHOUT YOU.
Yolei: THEY'VE BEEN
DOWN THERE A LONG TIME.
Davis: DON'T WORRY.
WE CAN COUNT ON CODY.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ALL CHEER ]
WAY TO GO!
THEY DESTROYED
THE DARK SPIRAL!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR CODY!
HIP-HIP...
All: HOORAY!
SO, THE DIGIDESTINED
MANAGED TO GET AWAY AGAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO ABOUT IT?
NOTHING.
YOU'RE NOT MAD?
THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
USUALLY, YOU WOULD HAVE
SMASHED SOMETHING BY NOW.
THIS IS ALL PART
OF THAT SECRET PLAN
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT,
ISN'T IT?
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
HA HA HA!
I GUESS WE SHOULD GET BACK
TO THE OTHERS NOW.
WHAT'S YOUR HURRY?
I WANT TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
I THINK YOU WERE AFRAID
OF THE OCEAN
BECAUSE IT WAS SOMETHING YOU
NEVER HAD THE CHANCE TO SEE.
IT'S TRUE SOME THINGS ABOUT
THE OCEAN ARE DANGEROUS,
BUT THERE ARE THINGS
DOWN HERE
THAT ARE MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN YOU COULD EVER IMAGINE.
LOOK UP AHEAD.
HEY, CODY.
YEAH?
TOGETHER, YOU AND I
CAN LEARN A LOT
ABOUT THE OCEAN.
YEAH!
LIKE I DON'T HAVE TO
BE AFRAID OF IT.
HA HA HA!
[ CODY GASPING ]
WHAT IS THE SECRET PLAN
OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
WILL IT FINALLY DESTROY
THE DIGIDESTINED?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."