ONCE STINGMON AND X-VEEMON
DNA DIGIVOLVE
TO FORM PAELDREMON,
OKUOMON WAS DEFEATED
SO EASILY,
WE FIGURED NO ONE
WOULD EVER STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST US AGAIN.
BUT WE BETTER BE CAREFUL --
AROKINIMON SWORE
SHE'D GET EVEN WITH US.
KEN'S CREST OF KINDNESS
HELPED US
GET OUT
OF A FEW JAMS ALREADY,
BUT I'M NOT SURE
OUR NEW FRIENDSHIP WILL LAST.
KEN SEEMS TO FEEL GUILTY
ABOUT THINGS HE DID
AS THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
BUT I DON'T THINK
FEELING GUILTY IS ENOUGH.
DAVIS WANTS US ALL
TO BE FRIENDS,
BUT I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO IT.
I HOPE WE DON'T NEED HIM
TO DEFEAT AROKINIMON.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Davis: WHOEVER DESTROYS
THE MOST CONTROL SPIRES
GETS A DATE WITH ME.
BY THE WAY, KARI'S
THE ONLY ONE ELIGIBLE.
V-LASER!
GREAT SHOT.
GRAND HORN!
TAIL HAMMER!
Both: GOLDEN NOOSE!
1, 2, AND 3.
Both: HA HA HA!
YEAH!
YEAH.
Davis: WOW. NICE GOING, GUYS.
I THINK MY DAD COULD USE YOU
ON HIS BOWLING TEAM.
Cody: HERE YOU GO, JUNK FOOD
FROM THE VENDING MACHINES --
CANDY BARS, POTATO CHIPS,
AND CHEESE CRACKERS.
BON APPéTIT.
COME ON, GUYS,
TAKE IT EASY.
YOU'LL GET A STOMACHACHE.
CHECK THIS OUT.
WHAT'S UP?
ANOTHER CONTROL SPIRE JUST
WENT DOWN IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
LOOKS LIKE KEN
IS WORKING OVERTIME.
HEY, GUESS WHO'S READY
FOR HIS SECOND COURSE?
YOU NEVER TOLD US
WHAT IT WAS LIKE
WHEN YOU DNA DIGIVOLVED
WITH WORMMON.
IT WAS WEIRD.
I FELT LIKE AN ACTION STAR
IN ONE OF THOSE BIG MOVIES.
WAS IT LIKE
WHEN YOU FIRST DIGIVOLVED
FROM ROOKIE
TO CHAMPION DIGIMON?
NO, BIGGER THAN THAT.
THE THING THAT WOULD
FREAK ME OUT THE MOST
WOULD BE TO HAVE TWO MINDS
AND ONE BODY.
IT'S STRANGE.
IT DIDN'T FEEL LIKE TWO MINDS
IN THE SAME BODY.
IT'S MORE
LIKE OUR MINDS MERGED
INTO ONE SUPER BEING.
SOUNDS WEIRD. YOU ALREADY
HAVE ENOUGH VOICES
RUNNING AROUND YOUR HEAD.
YEAH, IF I MERGED
WITH YOU,
I COULD GET LOST IN THERE
WITH THE OTHERS.
I WAS WONDERING HOW WEIRD
THE DNA DIGIVOLVE WAS
FOR DEMI-VEEMON.
IT CERTAINLY WAS STRANGE
FOR ME.
WELL, YOU TWO ARE CONNECTED.
YEAH. ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT YOU ARE
SOMEHOW CONNECTED, TOO?
THAT'S RIGHT.
PRETTY COOL.
I COULD EVEN FEEL
KEN'S HEART BEATING
RIGHT ALONG WITH MINE.
IT WAS KIND OF FREAKY,
TO BE HONEST.
SO YOU TWO WERE
ACTUALLY SYNCHRONIZED, THEN.
YOU MEAN LIKE THOSE GOOFY
SWIMMERS IN THE OLYMPICS?
NO.
SHE MEANS THAT YOUR HEARTS
WERE BEATING
AT THE EXACT SAME TIME,
SILLY.
I KNEW THAT, CODY.
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
I'M TELLING YOU,
JUST WHEN WE THINK
WE'VE GOT THIS WHOLE
DIGIVOLUTION THING FIGURED OUT,
SOMETHING NEW POPS UP.
BUT THIS IS THE CRAZIEST THING
WE'VE SEEN YET.
JUST THINK,
IF ALL THE DIGIMON
COULD DIGIVOLVE TOGETHER,
JUST IMAGINE ALL THE WEIRD
AND CRAZY COMBINATIONS.
LET'S SEE...
IF X-VEEMON
AND ANGEMON COMBINED,
THEY'D MAKE
ONE TOUGH-WINGED DIGIMON.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
OR HOW
ABOUT A GATOMON COMBO?
I DARE SOMEONE TRY TO PUT
THAT CAT OUT FOR THE NIGHT.
HOW ABOUT X-VEEMON
AND AQUILAMON,
OR EVEN X-VEEMON
AND ANKILOMON?
[ GASPS ]
WHAT, ARE YOU IMPLYING
THAT YOUR DIGIMON
IS TOO GOOD TO DNA
DIGIVOLVE WITH MINE?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT,
DAVIS.
I THINK WE NEED TO THINK
THIS THROUGH MORE
BEFORE WE GET TOO AHEAD
OF OURSELVES,
SO DON'T BITE OFF MY HEAD.
I'M TRYING TO BE SAFE.
AND I SEE IT AS A WAY
TO DEFEAT AROKINIMON.
I'M NOT SO SURE.
IT MIGHT BE DANGEROUS.
YOU'RE SO STUBBORN SOMETIMES,
CODY.
ARE YOU TWO FINISHED
BEING MACHO?
HEY, T.K.,
CHECK OUT DEMI-VEEMON.
I THINK HE'S LEARNED
A NEW BATTLE CRY.
[ SNEEZES ]
[ ALL LAUGH ]
Ken: BOY, I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW LATE IT IS.
I MUST HAVE FORGOTTEN
TO CHECK MY WATCH.
I GUESS TIME FLIES WHEN YOU'RE
DESTROYING CONTROL SPIRES.
YOU SEEM DISTRACTED.
KEN.
I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT THE DNA DIGIVOLVE,
AND I'M WORRIED
ABOUT THE AFTEREFFECTS.
IT DOES GIVE YOU THE POWER
OF AN ULTIMATE DIGIMON,
BUT AT WHAT PRICE?
IT COULD BE DRAINING YOUR POWERS
AND SHORTENING YOUR LIFE SPAN.
BUT, KEN, I DIDN'T FEEL
ANY SIDE EFFECTS
WHEN I DIGIVOLVED
WITH X-VEEMON,
THOUGH IT DID FEEL WEIRD
TO HAVE ONLY TWO LEGS.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST A THEORY NOW.
I DON'T HAVE ANY PROOF
TO SPEAK OF.
IF YOU DON'T WANT ME TO
DIGIVOLVE WITH THEM, I WON'T.
DO YOU REALLY HAVE
A THEORY ABOUT DIGIVOLVING,
OR DOES IT HAVE MORE TO DO
WITH HANGING OUT
WITH THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED?
[ Thinking ]
HE MIGHT BE RIGHT.
I'M JUST NOT SURE YET.
I KNOW. IT'S LATE.
[ Thinking ]
YOU DON'T FOOL ME, KEN.
YOU'RE REALLY JUST NERVOUS
ABOUT BEING WITH THE OTHERS.
YOU STILL HAVEN'T
FORGIVEN YOURSELF.
I GOT TO GET HOME.
MY PARENTS MUST BE WORRIED.
THEY PROBABLY THINK
I'VE DISAPPEARED AGAIN.
HURRY UP, WORMMON.
IT'S GETTING DARK
AND I DON'T WANT TO BE
A DIGI-DELICACY
FOR SOME FOREST CREATURE.
WAIT FOR ME.
IT'S AMAZING
HOW FAST YOU CAN MOVE
WHEN YOU HAVE
THE RIGHT MOTIVATION.
Arokinimon: LOOK AT WHAT
THESE LITTLE DEVIANTS HAVE DONE
TO MY PRECIOUS CONTROL SPIRES.
THEY THINK THEY'VE GOT
THE BEST OF ME, HUH?
WAIT TILL I GET MY HANDS
ON THEM.
THEY MAY HAVE SET MY PLANS
BACK A BIT,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
I'LL BE DEFEATED
BY SOME DIGIDESTINED
PIP-SQUEAKS.
I JUST HAVE TO BE
A LITTLE CRAFTIER NEXT TIME.
LOOK, THEY'VE KNOCKED
DOWN THE TOWERS
LIKE A ROW OF DOMINOES.
SO THEY WANT TO PLAY GAMES?
WE'LL PLAY ALL RIGHT,
BUT BY MY RULES.
I'LL SHOW THOSE BRATS
WHO'S BOSS.
HUH? WHAT'S THIS?
A VIDEO RECORDER OUT HERE?
IT LOOKS LIKE
THERE'S A TAPE INSIDE.
WHAT'S THIS?
Cody: I WONDER WHERE
THAT CREEPY WOMAN IS HIDING.
GOOD WORK. WE SMASHED
ALL THE CONTROL SPIRES
IN THIS AREA,
BUT THERE'S STILL A LOT MORE
WE HAVE TO DESTROY.
LET'S GET STARTED, DUDE.
Cody: I WONDER WHERE
THAT CREEPY WOMAN IS HIDING.
[ SCOWLS ]
WE SMASHED ALL CONTROL SPIRES
IN THIS AREA, BUT THERE'S...
OH, BE QUIET.
HOW DARE YOU TALK ABOUT ME
LIKE I'M SOME KIND OF WITCH.
I DRESS THIS WAY
TO MAKE A FASHION STATEMENT.
I THINK I'LL CALL SOME FRIENDS
OF MINE AND ASK THEM
TO TEACH THOSE BRATS
A LESSON IN MANNERS.
Davis: IT'S AN E-MAIL
FROM THAT SPOOKY WOMAN.
"DEAR DIGIDESTINED,
WE NEED TO TALK
"ABOUT THE DEBT YOU OWE
FOR DESTROYING MY PROPERTY.
MEET ME AT THE GIGAHOUSE."
Kari: YOU KNOW IT'S A TRAP.
WHY ARE WE GOING?
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO FACE THEM SOONER OR LATER.
AT LEAST THIS WAY
IT WON'T BE A BIG SURPRISE.
HURRY.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
Kari: DIGIPORT OPEN.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL SET.
NOW, WE ALL AGREE THAT
IF IT'S TOO DANGEROUS,
WE JUST TURN BACK.
LET'S GO.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS, GUYS.
♪ HERE WE GO! ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH-OH, OH-OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO! ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH, OH, OH ♪
Kari: NOW THAT IS
ONE BIG YELLOW HOUSE.
Yolei: MY QUESTION --
WHO IS THE BIG PERSON
THAT LIVES IN IT?
THIS IS GIGAHOUSE?
IT'S HUGE AND SPACIOUS.
IT MUST BE 200 FEET TALL.
IT'S AMAZING.
NO KIDDING.
Kari: COULD YOU IMAGINE
HAVING TO MOW THIS LAWN?
T.K.:
OR WASHING THOSE WINDOWS?
YOU'D NEED A HELICOPTER
TO GET UP THERE.
Yolei: WHY DO YOU THINK
AROKINIMON CALLED US HERE,
TO ATTACK US WITH A TEAM
OF BASKETBALL PLAYERS?
Davis: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
LET'S LOOK FOR A WAY IN.
SO YOU GUYS
GOT THE E-MAIL, TOO.
HEY.
YOU GUYS COME
FOR THE HOUSE PARTY?
SOME HOUSE PARTY, VEEMON.
TOO BAD THE HOSTESS WANTS
TO MAKE PIÑATAS OF HER GUESTS.
THIS IS A SET-UP.
WE FIGURED THAT, TOO.
I GUESS MISS CONGENIALITY
WANTS TO ELIMINATE
ALL OF HER ENEMIES
IN ONE SWOOP.
THAT'S WHY I THINK
IT'S A BAD IDEA
FOR YOU GUYS TO GO IN.
YOU SHOULD GO HOME.
THAT'S CRAZY. ARE YOU PLANNING
ON GOING IN BY YOURSELF?
THAT MAKES NO SENSE.
SHE'LL EAT YOU FOR LUNCH.
KEN HAS A POINT.
WE CAN'T JUST SIT HERE.
THIS MIGHT BE OUR BEST CHANCE
TO STOP HER.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
WE GO IN THERE
TO SCOPE THINGS OUT.
IF IT'S A TRAP,
THE REST OF US CAN BUST IN
AND HELP.
DAVIS, SINCE YOU AND KEN
ARE SO FIRED UP TO GO,
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS GO FIRST?
Both: MM-HMM.
COUNT ON ME, TOO.
GREAT IDEA.
GLAD I THOUGHT OF IT.
HUH?
WE'LL BE RIGHT OUT HERE.
IF THINGS GET TOO CRAZY,
SIGNAL,
AND WE'LL COME
TO THE RESCUE, OKAY?
I STILL THINK
IT'S A BETTER IDEA
IF I GO IN THERE ALONE,
GUYS.
NOT A CHANCE, KEN.
WE'RE DNA
DIGIVOLVED PARTNERS.
WE SHOULD REALLY BE
TOGETHER ON THIS.
IF THINGS GET HECTIC IN THERE,
YOU'LL REALLY NEED ME.
COOL YOUR JETS, GUYS,
OR YOU'RE GOING TO END UP
FIGHTING EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHY
I'M GOING ALONG, TOO.
LET'S GO. COME ON, GUYS.
FOLLOW ME.
LAST ONE IN
IS A ROTTEN DIGIEGG.
Wormmon: I WOULD HATE
TO BE A ROTTEN DIGIEGG.
Arokinimon: THOSE FOOLS.
I KNEW THEY'D WALK WILLINGLY
INTO MY TRAP.
HOW STUPID CAN YOU GET?
I'LL TRY NOT
TO DISAPPOINT THEM.
I'LL HAVE PLENTY
OF LOVELY HORRORS
IN STORE FOR THEM
ONCE THEY GET INSIDE.
IF I'M GOING TO HAVE GUESTS,
I'LL HAVE TO STRAIGHTEN UP.
SO LITTLE TIME,
SO MUCH DESTRUCTION.
WHOA!
HOW IN THE WORLD
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GET
IN THERE ANYWAY?
Davis: MAYBE WE SHOULD LOOK
UNDER THE DOORMAT.
MAYBE THERE'S A 40-FOOT KEY.
MAYBE AROKINIMON WILL TRY
TO DESTROY US
WITH A GIANT,
SUPER EVIL DIGIPIZZA.
LET'S JUST HOPE
THAT WOMAN WON'T USE US
AS THE TOPPINGS.
I'M VERY ALLERGIC
TO ANCHOVIES.
IT REMINDS ME OF THIS BOOK
CALLED "GULLIVER'S TRAVELS."
IT'S ABOUT THIS KID
WHO SELLS AN OLD COW
FOR SOME MAGIC BEANS
AND ENDS UP FIGHTING THIS GIANT.
NUH-UNH, THAT'S "JACK
AND THE BEANSTALK," SILLY.
I KNEW THAT, DUDE.
I WAS JUST JOKING.
YOU GUYS ARE CLASSIC.
YOU TWO FIGHT JUST LIKE
AN OLD MARRIED COUPLE.
Davis: DID YOU GUYS
HEAR SOMETHING?
Cody: MAYBE IT WAS
YOUR IMAGINATION.
Ken: I HEARD IT, TOO.
WE'RE NOT ALONE HERE.
SOUNDS LIKE CLICKING.
Wormmon: IT'S COMING
FROM THAT VENT OVER THE STOVE.
EW, YUCK.
IT'S AN ARMY OF BILKIMON.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
AN INFESTATION OF KILLER BUGS
TO RUIN THE CHARM
OF A SWEET LITTLE COTTAGE.
WAIT. THERE'S SOMETHING BIG
COMING THIS WAY.
WHAT IS IT, GATOMON?
A WEIRD BUZZING NOISE.
IT'S LIKE....
[ LOUD BUZZING ]
Gatomon: A SWARM
OF ANGRY KILLER BUGS.
THEY DON'T LOOK TOO PLEASED,
I MUST SAY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPION ♪
VEEMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
X-VEEMON.
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
WORMMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPION ♪
...STINGMON.
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
ARMADILLOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANKILOMON.
♪ DIGITAL MONSTERS --
DIGIMON ♪
I HATE ROACHES.
TAKE THAT AND THAT!
ALLEY-OOP!
I'M GETTING
WORN OUT HERE.
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM.
EVERY TIME I KNOCK ONE DOWN,
TWO MORE POP UP IN ITS PLACE.
WE NEED MORE FIREPOWER.
YOU HEARD HIM, KEN.
WE NEED A DNA DIGIVOLVER,
OR WE'RE GOING TO BE BUG FOOD
IN A MATTER OF MINUTES.
I THINK HE'S RIGHT
ABOUT THIS ONE, KEN.
WE'RE OVERMATCHED HERE.
Davis: KEN,
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
I CAN'T DO THIS
BY MYSELF, HEAR ME?
NO, WAIT!
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THERE'S SOMETHING WEIRD
ABOUT THOSE BUGS.
TAKE A LOOK FOR YOURSELF.
DO YOU SEE ANY DARK SPIRALS
OR BLACK GEARS ON ANY OF THEM?
AREN'T THEY MADE
FROM CONTROL SPIRES?
MAYBE SHE CREATED THEM
FROM SCRATCH.
HUH? SHE COOKS, TOO?
GO FIGURE.
IT'S TIME WE REALIZED
WE'RE OUTNUMBERED.
GOTTA GO, BOYS.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
AND PRONTO.
FOLLOW ME.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
T.K.: LOOK OUT
FOR THOSE STINGERS.
WHO ARE THOSE GUYS,
AQUILAMON?
THEY'RE FLYMON.
WHY ARE THEY CHASING US?
WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
TO THEM.
I DON'T HAVE
THE SLIGHTEST CLUE.
T.K. LOOK OUT!
WHAT'S THE PLAN, KARI?
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM.
SOONER OR LATER,
THEY'LL CATCH US.
HEAD FOR THE HOUSE.
THE WINDOW IS CLOSED.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
LEAVE THAT TO ME.
EQUUS BEAM!
T.K.: SORRY WE DIDN'T KNOCK.
PUT IT ON MY BILL.
AAH!
YOU BOYS STINK.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE SHOWER?
DON'T FORGET TO WASH
BEHIND YOUR EARS.
MAN, THOSE GUYS
GIVE ME THE WILLIES.
NICE WORK, X-VEEMON.
THAT'LL SHOW THOSE CREEPS.
SOMETHING TELLS ME WE'RE NOT
OUT OF HOT WATER YET, GUYS.
THIS PLACE HAS MORE BUGS IN IT
THAN A SECONDHAND COMPUTER.
KUNEMON -- THESE LARVA DIGIMON
HAVE A SHOCKING ATTACK --
THE ELECTRIC THREAD.
THEY'RE SMALL
BUT PACK QUITE A WALLOP.
YOU CREEPS
GIVE BUGS A BAD NAME.
STINGMON, LOOK OUT!
WHOA!
DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT YOU, KEN.
ARMADILLOMON, WE HAVE
TO ARMOR DIGIVOLVE RIGHT NOW.
I'M ALL OVER IT, CODY.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
GAMARIMON -- THE RELIABLE
GUARDIAN OF THE SEAS.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
THEY'RE IN THAT
GIGANTIC WASHING MACHINE.
NOW LET'S GO GET THEM.
HURRY!
HOLD ON TIGHT!
THEY'RE THEY ARE.
YOU GUYS NEED A RIDE?
HURRY. KEN'S RUNNING OUT
OF AIR.
KEN, WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
[ SCREAMING ]
GOING UP?
Davis: X-VEEMON,
FOLLOW THEM.
Aquilamon: HOW RUDE.
THERE'S TOO MANY
OF THOSE THINGS.
WE HAVE TO FIND
THE OTHERS.
BUT WHERE ARE THEY?
I THINK WE SHOULD SPLIT UP
AND SEARCH FOR THEM.
Kari: GOOD IDEA.
I'LL SEE YOU IN A FEW.
HEY, UGLIES, THIS WAY.
UH-OH, I THINK I MADE THEM
REALLY MAD NOW.
HEY, CODY, I'VE GOT
TO THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME
BACK THERE.
FOR A FEW SECONDS,
I THOUGHT I WAS A GONER.
THAT WAS PRETTY SLICK,
ARMADILLOMON.
THAT'S COOL, BUT I WAS JUST
PAYING YOU BACK.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE WHEN
WE FOUGHT THUNDERMON, REMEMBER?
I FIGURE IT WAS THE LEAST
WE COULD DO TO PAY YOU BACK.
Davis: OH, YEAH.
SO, THERE.
THEN WE'RE EVEN.
WE SHOULD GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THOSE THINGS
FIND OUT WHERE WE WENT.
WE'RE SITTING DUCKS HERE.
I AGREE, AND WE STILL HAVE
TO FIND THAT WOMAN.
HARD RIGHT.
QUEEN'S PAWN.
Kari: NICE SHOT.
IT'S A GIANT STUDY.
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT COMPUTER.
IZZY WOULD HAVE A FIELD DAY
WITH A MACHINE LIKE THAT.
WE GOT TO HIDE.
LUCKY I BRUSHED UP
ON MY DEWEY DECIMAL SYSTEM.
I THINK WE LOST THEM.
Ken: IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE
IS PLAYING A FLUTE.
IT'S COMING FROM THE ROOM
BEYOND THAT VENT.
DEAD END.
THE ONLY WAY AROUND IT
IS THROUGH IT.
STINGMON,
IF YOU'D BE SO KIND.
GLADLY.
WHAT A GENTLEMAN.
Davis: IT'S AROKINIMON.
SHE'S THE ONE PLAYING THE FLUTE.
Ken: WELL, I'M READY
TO SHOVE THAT FLUTE
RIGHT UP HER NOSE.
HEH HEH HEH.
SORRY WE DIDN'T BRING
A HOUSEWARMING GIFT.
WE'RE GOING TO END
YOUR REIGN OF TERROR
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
SUCH HARSH WORDS.
WHERE ARE YOUR MANNERS?
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT
THERE'S A LADY PRESENT?
I GUESS I'LL HAVE
TO TEACH YOU SOME RESPECT.
I OVERESTIMATED YOU KIDS.
IF I KNEW YOU'D WALK
WILLINGLY INTO A TRAP,
I WOULD HAVE
DONE THIS SOONER.
Ken: YOU'RE CORNERED.
OH, KEN,
YOU'RE SUCH A TOUGH GUY
WHEN YOU'RE IN FRONT
OF YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS.
DAVIS, IT'S TIME
TO DNA DIGIVOLVE.
CONSIDER IT DONE.
AAH!
Davis: DUDE, WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THE FLUTE PLAYING?
HAS SHE LOST IT?
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING, STINGMON?
[ GROANING ]
Cody: IT'S THE MUSIC
FROM THE FLUTE.
IT CAN SOMEHOW
CONTROL STINGMON.
SMART BOY.
ANY REQUESTS?
WE HAVE TO GET THAT FLUTE
AWAY FROM HER, ARMADILLOMON.
IT'S TIME FOR DIGMON.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF KNOWLEDGE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THIS.
SHE'S CONTROLLING
DIGMON, TOO.
CODY, LOOK OUT!
YOU CHILDREN DISAPPOINT ME.
OF COURSE THE FLUTE
CONTROLS THE DIGIMON,
BUT YOU STILL AREN'T
BRIGHT ENOUGH TO FIGURE OUT WHY.
ARE YOU THINKING
WHAT I'M THINKING?
YEP. I'VE GOT IT
ALL FIGURED OUT.
THE FLUTE ONLY CONTROLS
INSECT DIGIMON.
THAT'S WHY ONLY DIGMON
AND STINGMON
ARE AFFECTED BY IT.
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
SO WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO ABOUT IT NOW?
WHY DON'T YOU BE A SPORT
AND TAKE YOUR LUMPS,
GOGGLE BOY?
Yolei: WE'D BETTER
FIND THE OTHERS SOON.
THEIR AIM IS GETTING BETTER.
HELLO, BOYS.
Cody: DIGMON,
DON'T DO IT.
ROCK CRACKING.
AAH!
GUYS, I'M STUCK.
ME, TOO.
IT'S SOME KIND OF WEB.
YES. PARDON MY RUDENESS,
BUT THERE'S A VERY GOOD FRIEND
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET.
Davis: KEN, PLEASE TELL ME
THAT'S A DIGIMON FRIEND OF YOURS
WE'VE NEVER MET BEFORE
AND NOT A BIG RAVENOUS SPIDER.
SORRY, DAVIS.
Arokinimon: MEET TOKUGUMON,
AND SHE'S HUNGRY.
NO! LET ME GO!
GRRAAH!
Man: WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
GET OUT OF THIS STICKY
SITUATION?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."