CODY AND SUBMARIMON FOUND
THE EMPEROR'S UNDERWATER BASE AND FREED ALL OF HIS PRISONERS.
WHILE INSIDE THE BASE,
WE SAW A GIANT DARK WHIRLPOOL
THAT OUR DIGIMON SENSED
WAS EVIL.
SUDDENLY,
I SAW OUR OLD NEMESIS DEVIMON.
HE ALMOST DESTROYED US
ONCE BEFORE,
SO TO MAKE SURE
IT WOULDN'T HAPPEN AGAIN,
I FINALLY GAVE KEN
A PIECE OF MY MIND.
JUST THEN,
KEN UNLEASHED CHIMERAMON,
A DIGIMON HE CREATED
FROM THE STRONGEST PARTS
OF OTHER DIGIMON.
I HOPE HE'S NOT AS STRONG
AS HE THINKS HE IS, EITHER.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HEAT VIPER!
GRRAAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
NOW, THIS IS WHAT I CALL FUN!
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!
GO AHEAD AND RUN,
BUT THERE'S NOWHERE TO HIDE!
SOON I WILL HAVE CONTROL
OVER THE ENTIRE DIGITAL WORLD!
HEH HEH HEH HEH HEH HEH!
OH, MASTER...
[ Thinking ] IS THIS REALLY
WHAT KEN WANTS?
Girl: ANOTHER CITY DESTROYED.
THIS IS TERRIBLE!
Boy: KEN DOES A LOT OF DAMAGE
FROM HIS FLYING R.V.,
EVEN IF IT DOES LOOK LIKE
A GIANT FLYING SLUG!
ALL THOSE POOR DIGIMON
DON'T HAVE A HOME ANYMORE.
I'M TIRED OF BAD THINGS
HAPPENING TO GOOD DIGIMON.
WAIT TILL I GET
MY PAWS ON KEN.
HE'S DESTROYING
EVERYTHING IN HIS PATH!
AND HE SHOWS NO SIGNS
OF LETTING UP.
IT'S LIKE HE WANTS TO BURN
EVERY SQUARE INCH
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
BITE YOUR TONGUE!
I DON'T CARE WHAT IT TAKES.
I'M GOING TO FIND A WAY
TO STOP THAT THING.
T.K.'s RIGHT.
WE HAVE TO DESTROY IT,
NO MATTER WHAT IT COSTS US.
I THINK EVERYONE AGREES,
BUT EVEN WHEN WE ALL COMBINE,
WE STILL DON'T HAVE
THE POWER TO DEFEAT HIM.
SO NOW WHAT?
WE HAVE TWO OPTIONS --
QUIT OR GIVE UP --
BECAUSE NOTHING WILL STOP HIM
UNTIL HE RUNS OUT OF GAS.
HUH?
RUNS OUT OF GAS...
HMM.
TENTOMON, YOU JUST
GAVE ME AN IDEA.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO!
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
A PIPELINE.
HE'S CALLED CHIMERAMON?
HE HAS KABUTERIMON'S HEAD...
AND THE WINGS OF BOTH
ANGEMON AND AIRDROMON.
MONOCHROMON'S TAIL!
AND GARURUMON'S LEGS!
HE'S GOT GREYMON'S BODY
AND METALGREYMON'S HAIR.
AND KUWAGAMON'S, SKULLGREYMON'S,
AND DEVIMON'S ARMS!
TALK ABOUT A SPLIT PERSONALITY!
GEE, IT'S A GOOD THING
KARI SENT US THESE PICTURES
SO WE CAN GET
A GO LOOK AT HIM.
AND THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
BUILT THIS?
COULDN'T HE HAVE STAYED
WITH MODEL AIRPLANES, LIKE US?
THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING TO DESTROY HIM.
HEY, IZZY,
HOW DO I DESTROY HIM?
BEFORE WE DO THAT,
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET HIM TO HOLD STILL.
HOW DO WE DO THAT?
HIS BASE IS ALWAYS MOVING.
WE'RE GETTING ANOTHER E-MAIL
FROM CODY.
"WE FOUND A PIPELINE THAT WILL
CROSS PATHS WITH KEN'S BASE.
I KNOW YOU CAN USE
THIS INFORMATION SOMEHOW."
HMPH!
HE HAS SUCH CONFIDENCE IN ME!
WHAT PIPELINE?
HEY, LOOK.
WHAT'S THAT A PICTURE OF?
I'LL CHECK.
OH, I GET IT.
THE PIPELINE IS CONNECTED
TO THE OFFSHORE OIL PLATFORM.
AN OIL PIPELINE...
PIPELINE...
I'VE GOT IT!
YOU FIGURED OUT
HOW TO STOP HIM?
ACTUALLY, NO,
BUT I NEEDED AN 8-LETTER WORD
FOR MY CROSSWORD PUZZLE.
STAY ON TRACK.
OH, RIGHT. ACTUALLY,
I DO HAVE A PLAN
THAT, IF WE'RE LUCKY,
JUST MIGHT WORK.
LET'S HOPE THESE GUYS
CAN PULL IT OFF.
I SHOULD BUILD A MONUMENT
TO MYSELF.
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
[ Gasps ] UHH!
MASTER, WHAT'S WRONG?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
[ PANTING ]
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A TIME-OUT
FROM ALL THE DESTRUCTION?
YOU CAN START AGAIN
TOMORROW.
GO AWAY.
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
Voice: YOU CAN'T HIDE
FROM THE DARKNESS!
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M WORMMON.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
WATCH YOUR STEP,
OR YOU MIGHT FALL INTO A HOLE
THAT YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WAS THERE!
AAH!
Wormmon: MASTER, WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ CRAZY LAUGHTER ]
NOW THAT I HAVE CHIMERAMON,
NOTHING CAN STOP ME
FROM RULING THIS WORLD,
NOT EVEN SOME STUPID VOICE.
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!
DO YOU THINK
ANYONE SPOTTED US?
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
LET'S GO TOPSIDE
AND SCOUT THE SITUATION.
COME ON!
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
LET'S GO BELOW AND HIDE!
GRRAAH!
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
I WANT TO GO HOME!
NO! WE HAVE TO FOLLOW
IZZY'S PLAN!
GET READY.
HERE HE COMES!
[ GROWLING ]
LET'S DO IT!
ALL RIGHT! GO FOR IT!
PAPA BREATH!
BLUE BLASTER!
WHERE DID THESE FLAMES
COME FROM?
HURRY AND GET
THE FIRE EXTINGUISHER!
VERY EFFICIENT,
GABUMON!
THANKS, AGUMON.
YOU WERE PRETTY HOT YOURSELF.
WHAT AM I -- INVISIBLE?
SO SUE ME --
I DON'T HAVE DRAGON'S BREATH!
LET'S SEE YOU GUYS
TRY FLYING!
Girl: LOOK!
IZZY'S PLAN WORKED!
WELL, THE FIRST PART
OF IT, ANYWAY.
WHILE HE'S BUSY TAKING CARE
OF HIS EMERGENCY,
WE'LL SNEAK IN!
HEY, GUYS, LOOK DOWN THERE.
DO YOU SEE THAT SMALL DOOR?
I BET THAT'S THE ENTRANCE!
LET'S GO, RADRUMON! YEAH!
AM I GOOD, OR WHAT?
IF HE KEEPS
TELLING HIMSELF THAT,
HE MIGHT START
TO BELIEVE IT!
AT LEAST SOMEONE WILL.
WE'VE DONE EVERYTHING
WE CAN. NOW WHAT?
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
LEFT TO DO.
YEAH, LET'S HIT
THE SUSHI BAR!
PART ONE OF THE PLAN
WENT WELL.
GREAT.
WILL THEY BE OKAY?
THEY'RE IN THE MOST DANGEROUS
POSSIBLE PLACE.
WE'RE JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO TRUST THEM.
THIS TIME
THEY'RE ON THEIR OWN.
GOOD LUCK, YOU GUYS.
WE BETTER GET READY
FOR A LONG NIGHT.
I DON'T THINK ANY OF US
ARE GOING TO SLEEP.
I BET THE DIGIMON EMPEROR WON'T,
AND I KNOW DAVIS AND THE OTHERS
WON'T SLEEP, EITHER.
[ Yawns ] I'M EXHAUSTED.
LET'S STOP AND SLEEP.
NOT YET. LET'S KEEP GOING
A LITTLE FURTHER.
HEY, GUYS, LOOK!
THERE'S A LIGHT
AT THE END OF THE TUNNEL.
COULDN'T YOU THINK OF SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE ORIGINAL?
HEY, LOOK AT THAT!
WOW! IT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
OUT OF A SCIENCE FICTION MOVIE!
AND I'M THE HOTSHOT PILOT
WHO RESCUES PRINCESS KARI!
Kari: HE SAID SCIENCE FICTION,
NOT FANTASY.
[ GASPS ]
BOY, I BET HE GETS
GREAT RECEPTION
WITH THAT TV ANTENNA.
AND HE MUST GET ALL
THE UNDERGROUND STATIONS
WITH THAT ONE.
DOWN THERE -- THAT'S WHERE
THE ENGINE ROOM IS.
FIGURES. HOW COME
THE ENGINE ROOM
IS NEVER
ON THE SAME FLOOR
AS THE FRONT DOOR?
LOOK, MASTER,
WE HAVE MORE GUESTS.
SHOULD I PUT TOGETHER
ANOTHER HORS D'OEUVRE TRAY?
HOW CONVENIENT.
I CAN FINISH OFF THOSE KIDS
WITHOUT LEAVING HOME.
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
LOOK -- BAKEMON!
AT LEAST THEY'RE SMALL.
SOMETHING TELLS ME
THEY'RE NOT HERE TO WELCOME US.
CODY'S RIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
WE'LL WELCOME THEM INSTEAD!
THUNDER BLAST!
WHOAAH!
GOLD RUSH!
OOH! AAH!
EAGLE EYE!
AAH!
QUEEN PAW!
WHOA! AAH!
MANE WIND!
LET'S LEAVE WHILE
THE GHOSTS ARE SPOOKED.
WHAT'S YOUR HURRY?
WOW, THIS PLACE IS HUGE!
I BET KEN PLAYS SOCCER IN HERE.
WITH WHO?
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ GROWLING ]
IT'S CHIMERAMON.
GRRAAH!
MORE BAKEMON?
WHAT DID KEN DO,
BUY THEM BY THE DOZEN?
WE WERE ALMOST
IN THE ENGINE ROOM.
DAVIS, YOU AND THE OTHERS
GO AND HIDE.
CHIMERAMON
IS REALLY STRONG.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
ALL OF US TO FIGHT,
AND IT MIGHT GET UGLY.
I AGREE.
STAY CLEAR, T.K.
YOU GUYS BE CAREFUL.
DON'T WORRY, KARI.
I'LL TRY.
SAVE US SOME SNACKS
FOR WHEN THIS IS ALL OVER!
LET'S GO, GUYS.
WE CAN HIDE OVER HERE.
THUNDER BLAST!
EAGLE EYE!
QUEEN PAW!
MANE WIND!
ALL RIGHT!
LOOK!
GOLD RUSH!
GREAT JOB.
THANKS A LOT, DIGMON!
DON'T MENTION IT.
HEAT VIPER!
HE'S TOO POWERFUL.
AND THEY WEREN'T EVEN HIT!
HE DOESN'T CARE WHO HE HITS.
HE'S TOTALLY OUT OF CONTROL.
MASTER, AT THIS RATE,
HE'LL DESTROY
THE WHOLE BASE.
I DON'T CARE!
THUNDER BLAST!
GOLD RUSH!
TEMPEST WING!
STAR SHOWER!
ROSETTA STONE!
WE GOT HIM!
[ SNARLING ]
IT HAD NO EFFECT.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THEY USED THEIR BEST ATTACKS,
AND HE DOESN'T HAVE A SCRATCH!
NOW WHAT?
WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO
RIGHT NOW EXCEPT WATCH.
HEAT VIPER!
THEY CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE.
HE'LL DESTROY THEM!
I'VE GOT THAT SHRINKING FEELING.
UH-OH.
UPAMON!
OHH...HARUMPH.
OOH!
POROMON! OH, NO!
DAVIS!
DEMIVEEMON!
I CAN'T HOLD IT!
GATOMON!
PATAMON!
WAIT A MINUTE.
THOSE LITTLE DIGIMON...
I'VE SEEN THEM BEFORE.
[ Gasps ] NOW I REMEMBER.
IT WAS AT THAT SOCCER GAME
WHEN I FIRST MET THOSE KIDS.
THEY'RE SO LITTLE.
THAT'S RIGHT --
JUST LIKE HUMAN BABIES.
WHAT?
I NEVER
THOUGHT OF IT BEFORE.
HUMAN BABIES?
CHIMERAMON, STOP!
[ GROWLING STOPS ]
HE STOPPED MOVING!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
LET'S GO!
I'LL DEAL WITH THOSE KIDS
ON MY OWN.
MASTER...
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU MEAN LEAVE?
OUR PLAN DIDN'T WORK
BECAUSE OUR DIGIMON
WEREN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO
COME UP WITH A NEW PLAN
AND TRY AGAIN.
BESIDES, THEY DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH STRENGTH TO KEEP GOING.
I'M WITH T.K.
WELL, I'M NOT!
All: HUH?
LOOK, GUYS, WE CAN'T JUST
GIVE UP AND LEAVE NOW.
WE MIGHT NOT EVER
GET A CHANCE LIKE THIS AGAIN.
AND HOW DO WE KNOW
HE WON'T START ATTACKING AGAIN?
HE'S JUST STANDING THERE
LIKE A BIG UGLY STUFFED ANIMAL!
LET'S FINISH
WHAT WE CAME HERE TO DO!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
KARI'S RIGHT.
OUR DIGIMON HAVE RETURNED
TO THEIR IN-TRAINING FORMS.
WE DIDN'T MEAN TO.
I JUST CAN'T FORGET
WHAT HAPPENED.
WE HAD TO SIT AROUND AND WATCH
AS THIS MIX-N-MATCH MONSTER
DESTROYED EVERYTHING,
AND IT DIDN'T MATTER
WHO GOT IN HIS WAY.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I CAN'T
LET THAT HAPPEN AGAIN.
IF NONE OF YOU WANT TO GO
WITH ME, I'M GOING IN ALONE,
BECAUSE I REFUSE TO GIVE UP
UNTIL THIS THING IS DESTROYED
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
I'M GOING WITH YOU, DAVIS.
ARE YOU SURE?
COME ON.
DO YOU REALLY HAVE TO ASK?
ALL RIGHT, THEN, LET'S GO!
HOLD ON! LET ME PUT ON
MY SAFETY BELT!
OW! THAT'S NOT A SAFETY BELT,
THAT'S MY HAIR!
MAYBE THIS WASN'T A GOOD IDEA.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WELL, I GUESS IT'S OUR TURN.
IF DAVIS THINKS HE'S GOING
TO TAKE ALL THE CREDIT,
HE CAN FORGET IT!
YEAH, HE'D TAKE CREDIT
FOR INVENTING THE WHEEL.
CHIMERAMON,
DON'T LET THEM GET AWAY!
IT'S THE DIGIMON EMPEROR!
[ GROWLING ]
CHIMERAMON,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
CHIMERAMON!
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S THAT WEIRD VOICE?
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
KEN, WHAT'S WRONG?
KEN --
LEAVE ME ALONE!
[ Thinking ] I HAVE NOTHING
TO BE SCARED OF.
THE POWERS OF DARKNESS
MEAN NOTHING TO ME.
I'M STILL THE RULER
OF THIS WORLD!
KEN WAS DOING THINGS
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN DOING.
I WISH HE WOULD
LISTEN TO ME.
ONCE I FIND CHIMERAMON,
NOTHING CAN STOP ME!
NOW I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN PROTECT HIM.
WORMMON, LET'S SEE
WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
KEN MUST HAVE TRIED TO CONTROL
THE POWERS OF DARKNESS,
BUT IT WAS TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
THIS IS OUR CHANCE
TO GET TO THE ENGINE ROOM
AND DESTROY IT.
NEXT TIME, YOU CLIMB
AND I'LL SIT ON YOUR HEAD.
THAT LOOKS LIKE THE ENGINE ROOM.
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE!
THIS WAY.
THE ENGINE ROOM
IS OVER HERE.
FOLLOW ME.
DO I LOOK STUPID TO YOU?
THIS IS SOME KIND OF TRAP!
NO. YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
THIS ISN'T A TRAP.
I'M TRYING
TO SAVE MY MASTER.
HE CREATED THIS AWFUL
DIGIMON -- CHIMERAMON --
AND NOW HE CAN'T
CONTROL IT ANYMORE.
I'M AFRAID THINGS
HAVE GONE TOO FAR,
AND I'M LOSING HIM.
I HOPE IF YOU
DESTROY THIS PLACE,
I'LL GET HIM BACK.
I'M WILLING TO HELP YOU
IF YOU'LL HELP ME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
YOU WILL?
SURE. I'M NOT AS BIG A JERK
AS PEOPLE THINK.
REALLY? YOU'RE NOT?
THANKS! COME ON!
DO YOU FEEL THAT?
IT'S LIKE THE WHOLE ROOM
IS FULL OF SOME KIND OF ENERGY!
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S COMING
FROM THAT BLACK THING!
Wormmon: KEN FOUND THAT.
SOMEHOW THE POWER FROM IT
IS MAKING THIS BASE MOVE.
SO WE TAKE IT AWAY,
AND THEN THE BASE
WILL STOP MOVING.
WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO LIFT IT.
HUH?
THE POWER SOURCE!
WAY TO GO, DAVIS!
I GOT A WEIRD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ GRUNTING ]
DAVIS, LOOK AT THAT!
HUH?
YOU DIGIVOLVED! HOW?
AAH!
VEEMON, LOOK AT THAT!
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT!
ME NEITHER!
OH, MAN, IT LOOKS LIKE
A GOLDEN DIGIEGG.
I GUESS THIS MEANS
THAT IT'S MINE.
VEEMON,
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT?
YEAH! MM-HMM!
GOLDEN ARMOR ENERGIZE!
VEEMON GOLDEN ARMOR
DIGIVOLVE, TOO!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
MAGNAMON!
OH, DUDE, THAT'S AMAZING!
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
THIS CHANGES EVERYTHING.
AAH...
Magnamon: THE BALANCE OF POWER
HAS SHIFTED.
WILL MAGNAMON BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT CHIMERAMON?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON" -- DIGITAL MONSTERS.