DAVIS:
ExVeemon and I decided
to take on MaloMyotismon,
even though the others
were afraid of him.
I don't blame them.
If ever stopped
to think about anything,
I'd be scared too!
MaloMyotismon played
mind tricks on everyone,
terrifying Ken
and making the others
believe their favorite
wish had come true!
But my wish really
did come true
because Veemon digivolved
into all his forms
at the same time!
That's the good news.
The bad news is that
MaloMyotismon's wishes
are also coming true,
and his wishes could make
a genie crawl back
in his bottle!
(electronic music)
♪ Di di di ♪
♪ Digimon Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Change into
digital champions ♪
♪ to save
the digital world ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
Digivolve into champions
Armor,
digivolve
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are
the champions ♪
♪ Digimon digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon ♪
TAI:
It's so dark,
and it'll be like
this forever
if we can't stop
MaloMyotismon.
No, I can't give up hope.
I have too many people
depending on me.
The two worlds will
unite in darkness!
(laughs)
Then they shall
both be mine!
That's never going
to happen!
MALOMYOTISMON:
And why not?
Cause we're gonna
stop you!
Once and for all!
MALOMYOTISMON:
You fools!
You think you can defeat me?
Your pitiful light
is no match
for my darkness.
Even now it consumes
the world.
Not for long!
Get him!
IMPERIALDRAMON:
Positron Laser!
Screaming Darkness!
(screaming)
They're losing.
And it's all our fault.
GIRL:
Thanks to us,
the Digital World
and the real world
are going to be covered
in darkness.
You foolish DigiDestined.
Watch closely now.
Your world is being
consumed by eternal night.
You'll never win.
Even if you defeat us,
others will rise up
against you.
Who could possibly
beat him?
I just wanna go home.
Why bother?
There's no point.
I don't think any
of us have a home
to go home to anymore.
Yeah, there's no point
to anything anymore.
Hey, quit talking
like that.
Why? It's all true,
isn't it?
There's nothing any
of us can do to win.
LITTLE BOY:
He's right,
there's no point
in trying.
The only thing we'll do
is fail.
He beat us,
it's just that simple.
No, he hasn't!
GROUP: Huh?
But he will beat us
if you give up!
Just because things
look bad,
that's no reason not
to try!
I don't know.
Well, I do.
So quit sitting there like
a bunch of sad sacks
and let's beat this guy!
But what can we do?
He's already defeated
us once.
You're right.
It's hopeless.
In mere moments both
worlds will be mine!
(laughs)
The darkness
is strong here too.
I know, but if we want
to get back
to the Digital World,
this is our only way.
It might be
the only chance
for all of us
in both worlds.
For everything.
But we don't have any idea
if this gate is going to open!
But the gate in Tokyo
is sealed by BlackWarGreymon.
This is the closest one.
I know he was trying
to help us protect
the Digital World.
I think he may've done
more harm than good
if we can't get
back there.
It looks like
we have no choice
but to give it a try
and hope for the best.
This is the place
where we first went
to the Digital World.
Maybe that's a good sign.
Well, this had better work.
We have to get Noriko
to Oikawa as soon as possible.
Tell me,
what's going to happen
to my daughter
if you don't?
Don't worry,
she'll be fine.
But‐‐
She'll be okay,
I promise.
FATHER:
Alright, we trust you.
SORA:
Am I the only one
who's worried we won't
be able to save her?
That we won't be able
to save everything?
The dying of the light,
and no one to rage against it.
My power over both
of the worlds
is growing stronger,
and now there's nothing
that can stand against me!
I don't think so.
Positron Laser!
Static Force!
Justice Beam!
Screaming Darkness!
(grunting and screaming)
MALOMYOTISMON: (laughs)
Why do they bother trying
to fight him?
There's just nothing
that they can do
that will defeat him.
They should know it's
all pointless by now.
Maybe we could help
if we were
the DigiDestined,
but we were only chosen
by Oikawa.
ALL: It's hopeless.
Tai, we have to get
to the Digital World,
before it's too late.
I know.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Digiport open!
Please?
MATT:
I guess our parents were wrong.
That's not the magic word
after all.
JOE:
This is bad, guys.
What are we gonna do?
This could be
the end of everything.
IZZY:
Whoa, wait a minute.
Look at this.
BOTH: Huh?
More bad news?
Gates are opening
all over the world!
Look, you guys.
It's lighting up like
a modem router
in full pulse mode!
MATT:
Well, if that looks like
a Christmas tree lighting up,
I'd have to agree with you.
SORA:
Look, the light from the gates
is cutting through
MaloMyotismon's blanket
of darkness!
IZZY:
It must be coming from Digivices
all over the planet!
MATT:
Just think, millions of kids
are banding together
to take a stand
against MaloMyotismon
right now.
It doesn't matter
where they're from,
or what language they speak.
They all knew they had
unite against the darkness,
had to fight it no matter
how futile it may have seemed.
TAI:
I knew that MaloMyotismon
couldn't win that easily.
The whole world's
fighting him!
(gasps)
KARI: Look!
So many Digimon!
DAVIS:
I hope we don't have
to feed em all!
There must be hundreds!
The light from
the Digivice has guided us.
It led us all here.
It's great!
The partner Digimon
are DigiDestined from
all over the world
are gathering.
We can't allow you
to destroy our world!
Yeah, you think
you can bully us?
Well, put up your dukes!
MALOMYOTISMON:
Your meaningless
little gathering
of buffoons
doesn't frighten me.
It doesn't matter how
many of you there are.
You'll never defeat me!
Screaming Darkness!
(screaming)
We have
to fight him, Mimi,
but I need your help!
I'm right here for you,
Palmon!
Tortomon!
Centarumon!
Frigimon!
Freezemon!
Shakomon!
Go, Apemon!
Meramon!
Crabmon!
Floramon!
Lunamon!
‐ Seamon!
‐ Kuwagamon!
Gotsumon!
MALOMYOTISMON:
Wait a minute.
What's happening?
The light!
It's blinding!
No, it can't be!
Hey look,
he's in pain.
The light of the Digimon
is winning!
MALOMYOTISMON:
(screams)
TAI:
Look, in the sky!
That light...
Just like three years ago.
The gate is opening up!
JOE:
It actually opened?
I mean,
of course it opened!
Come on, Noriko!
It's alright.
(grunts)
Let's go. Come on!
Yeah!
(beeping)
FATHER: Huh?
Noriko? Noriko?
Where did she go?
Don't you worry.
Your daughter's
in the very best of hands now.
Yes, but‐‐
There's nothing we can
really do right now,
but believe in the strength
of our children.
She's right, we'll
have to trust them.
I'm sure everything
will be fine.
It all worked out three
years ago, after all.
I hope so.
But tell me, what's gonna happen
if they don't come back?
We can't think like that.
If we want them to succeed,
we have to believe in them.
Everyone must believe.
Our children and the whole
world might depend on it.
DAVIS:
All the Digimon have fallen
into some kind of trance!
They look like Izzy when
he plays video games!
CODY:
They're absorbing the energy
from the beams of light,
like recharging
a battery on a laptop.
Look!
AGUMON: Hi, guys!
BOTH: Whoa!
Hey, look who we brought!
DigiDestined from
all over the world!
Who would've thought
there'd be so many?
The gates opened up
from all over the world,
and they came
to help us out.
And each one of them
has a partner Digimon
who wants
to help out too!
The bond between
the Digidestined
and the Digimon
opened up the gate!
MALOMYOTISMON: (growls)
I knew it was true.
We were never really meant
to be the DigiDestined.
We're not good enough.
What are you talking about?
Well, we don't have partner
Digimon like you guys have.
And all of us
are tainted.
We still carry
the dark spores inside of us.
LITTLE BOY:
Because of them, the only thing
we have to look
forward to is more pain.
KARI:
Oh no, the darkness
is returning!
Yes, just keep thinking
that way, my children.
You guys, he's getting
stronger!
It doesn't matter if you don't
have partner Digimon.
It doesn't matter
if you're not DigiDestined.
You don't need any of that stuff
to have a really good life.
That's easy
for you to say.
You have a Digimon.
We've all got
shortcoming's to face,
and problems we
wish we didn't have,
but you can't just
lie down
and give into all
of your troubles.
Look at Ken,
he didn't give up
when learned Oikawa
was using him.
Everyone has problems,
but everyone has good things
going for them too.
Yeah, but what do we have?
What about all your hopes?
And all of your dreams?
I think they're gone.
Or been taken away.
Geez, could you kids be
a little more negative?
The only person who can
take your dreams away is you
by giving up on them!
So, what's your dream?
Well? I wanna open
a noodle cart!
T. K. AND TOLEI: Huh?
Yeah! What's the matter
with that?
I wanna make the best noodles
in the whole wide world!
That's great, Davis!
Well, actually I...
I always wanted to be
a kindergarten teacher.
Me too.
(groaning in pain)
How about you?
A baseball player!
Agh!
I've always wanted
a bakery.
I love the smell
of fresh bread.
Agh!
I wanted
to draw comic books,
but everyone used
to laugh at me,
so I gave up on it.
Gyah!
I get it!
We all had dreams,
but somehow got
the idea
they were worthless,
so we gave up on them
when we shouldn't have.
Right?
Yeah, you can't
let other people
talk you out
of your dreams!
I wish we hadn't wasted
all this time by giving up.
Don't worry!
It's never too late
to go out
and make your dreams
become a reality!
Do you think that
even kids like us
can make our dreams
come true?
Of course! You bet!
Even me?
GROUP: Absolutely!
GROUP: Absolutely for real?
ALL:
Absolutely for real!
(Screaming in pain)
I feel so much happier!
I feel like I can do
anything now!
You can if you believe!
I do!
I believe in myself now!
GROUP: Huh?
Hey there, guys.
Well, aren't you glad
to meet your partner Digimon?
Thanks for believing in us.
A Digivice?
‐ For me?
‐ It's hard to believe.
DAVIS:
What's hard to believe
is how smart a handsome guy
like me can be.
YOLEI:
And humble.
NORIKO:
They're beautiful.
No!
This can't be happening!
These paltry children
can't make me disappear!
I won't allow it!
Quick, everybody.
Use your Digivices
and we'll get
rid of this pesky
darkness forever.
Giga Crusher!
(digital sounds)
We did it!
(cheering)
We destroyed him!
Hey, it's Gennai.
I have a present for you.
Here.
It's my tail ring!
Your tail ring was quite an
important little item,
Gatomon.
It kept the dark powers
of the Digimon emperor's
fortress
from growing out of control,
and it allowed you all
to DNA Digivolve.
And since that's not
necessary anymore,
you get to have it back,
but do me
a little favor.
No big deal, but if you could
keep it away from
the power‐hungry
evil creatures
looking to take over
and destroy the world,
that'd be great.
In all seriousness,
you truly saved the world.
Thank you, to all of you.
We went
to another world too,
different than
the real or digital worlds.
What was that weird place?
Believe it or not,
it's a world that can
grant people's wishes.
Well actually, it is
the power to grant wishes.
Huh?
You know,
the Digital World
also has some of that power
to make dreams come true.
So the Digital World is
basically a mix of digital data
and people's dreams.
I see.
And that ocean, maybe
it has the power
to bring people's
dark thoughts to life.
What about
the dark spores?
Shouldn't they all be taken out?
No, it's all right.
As long as we believe
in ourselves and our dreams,
the dark spores will remain
powerless against us.
That's great, Ken.
(gasps)
Cody!
What are you doing?
CODY: (grunting)
Almost there.
Don't give up.
Just a little further,
Mr. Oikawa.
Don't give up now.
I don't know if I can.
CODY:
Get up. You have to try.
We're almost
in the Digital World.
Thank you, Cody.
If only
I had your optimism,
I might not have ended up
with such a sad fate,
but I was unable
to maintain hope
through the bad times,
and I drowned in my despair.
If only I'd had
friends like you,
or allowed myself
to have them.
GREEN DIGIMON: Yukio!
What's this?
Who is this Digimon?
I'm Datirimon.
I'm Yukio's partner
Digimon.
Oikawa's partner
Digimon?
Hey, check it out!
This little guy's
here for you, Oikawa!
He's mine?
It's been a long time.
I've been waiting
practically forever.
He's mine.
I don't believe it.
Wait a minute.
Don't you remember me?
Of course.
I remember you.
It's just been so long
since I've seen you,
since my happier days
with Hiroki.
DATIRIMON:
Well, better late than never!
Come into the Digital World.
CODY:
This is your chance.
All you have to do is
stand up and walk into
the Digital World.
Come on!
GENNAI: He may not have
the strength, Cody.
His body was badly damaged
by having MaloMyotismon
inside of him.
I'm afraid he doesn't
have much time left.
But no!
Is that the Digital World?
It seem so rough.
Somehow unfinished.
GENNAI:
A lot of energy was used up
to defeat MaloMyotismon,
and as a result,
the Digital World itself
has been weakened.
I'm afraid it's going to take
a lot of hard work
to get it back to the way
it used to be before
all of this happened.
The power
of the other world.
(grunting)
The other world?
We can use it
to make dreams come true.
So what do you plan to do?
My body is too weak
to go on,
but I won't need it.
Wait, there must be
another way!
Hold on to your optimism,
and your dreams,
and especially your
friends, Cody.
Perhaps if I had been
more like you,
I could've had adventures too.
You still can!
You finally made it
to the Digital World
and found your partner
Digimon, didn't you?
Mr. Oikawa!
Are you going so soon?
But we just met again.
OIKAWA: Don't worry,
I'll always be here inside
the Digital World.
I shall protect it.
Goodbye, DigiDestined,
and thank you.
T. K.:
Oikawa transformed himself
into energy,
and used his life force
to revitalize
the Digital World.
He restored all of the beauty
that was almost completely
destroyed
by MaloMyotismon,
and Oikawa's spirit
is still there
protecting
the Digital World forever.
Hey, Dad.
Come on already,
we have to go.
Right, we don't wanna
be late.
T. K.:
25 years have passed,
and I've become a novelist.
I'm working
on a series of books
about our adventures
in the Digital World.
There've been a lot
of big changes in the world,
and in us since then.
Hey everybody,
look, it's T. K.!
GROUP: Hello!
(greetings)
T. K.:
Now everyone on the planet
knows about
the Digital World,
and has their own
partner Digimon,
but despite all
the changes
that contact with
the Digital world has brought,
one thing has remained
the same: our friendship.
We all still get together,
and those gatherings
are some of the happiest times
of my life.
Tai and Agumon are diplomats
dealing with relations between
the real and digital worlds.
(chuckles)
and Tai finally cut his hair.
‐ Hey, you wanna play tag?
‐ Yeah.
T. K.: Matt and Gabumon became
an astronaut team
and made it all the way to
Mars,
even though they were only
supposed to go to the Moon.
Now be careful, son.
Aw, how come?
I'll take care of him.
Okay, and I'll take care
of you.
T. K.: Sora and Biyomon are
fashion designers.
Biyomon says their new line
is just to die for.
Try to stay clean.
Nah, go roll in the mud.
T. K.: Joe's the DigiWorld's
first doctor.
Too bad his patients keep
eating his tongue depressors.
Now, remember to share with
the other kids.
Right.
T. K.:
Mimi's cooking show
is the only time
she takes off her hat.
Make sure you don't
act like a ram cache.
Or a SIM chip.
T. K.:
Izzy researches the DigiWorld.
He and his daughter
have their own language.
‐ Ready to have fun?
‐ Mhm!
T. K.: Kari's a teacher. She
actually likes being in school.
Now, whatever happens,
don't get all panicky, okay?
LITTLE BOY: But Mom, that's
what you always do.
(laughing)
T. K.: Yolei and Ken are married
with children,
and Ken and Stingmon
are detectives,
but Yolei says he
can't seem to detect
when it's his turn
to do the dishes.
Hey Dad, can I sue
if I get tagged it?
T. K.:
Cody's a defense attorney.
He's bought
a hundred briefcases
cause Armadillomon
keeps sitting on them.
Hey, everybody!
Sorry we're late.
(greetings)
T. K.: Well, Davis finally
opened his noodle cart,
and believe it or not,
it became a huge success.
There are now "Noodle Noodle
Come Get Your Noodle" carts
all over the world.
What are you doing here
standing with your dad?
Go play tag!
Yeah, go show em
what tag's all about!
Alright!
So are you guys ready?
GROUP: Mhm.
DAVIS'S SON: Come on, everybody.
Let's do it!
T. K.: So, you can see
we're still having adventures.
They're just
a little different
than the ones we used
to have when we were kids.
The darkness has
not been conquered,
and it will continue to fight
against the light forever,
but as long as people remember
to follow their dreams,
evil will be kept at bay.
And on days like today,
it's hard to see any
darkness anywhere.
Now it's up to our children,
and to children everywhere
to follow their dreams.
Who know where
they'll end up?
But the only way to find out is
to take that first step
into adventure.
(children speaking)
(Digimon theme music)