ARUKENIMON SAID
SHE WOULD RELEASE
THE KIDNAPPED CHILDREN
IF I WENT WITH HER WILLINGLY.
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
IT'S PROBABLY GOOD I WENT
BECAUSE I FOUND OUT
THIS CREEPY MAN NAMED OWIKAWA
HAD BEEN BEHIND EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED TO ME.
HE'S TRYING TO RUIN THE LIVES
OF OTHER KIDS
WITH HIS DISGUSTING
DARK SPORES.
AS IF THAT WASN'T ENOUGH,
THE OTHERS ACTUALLY HAD
TO DESTROY SOME EVIL DIGIMON
WHO WERE TAKING
INNOCENT PEOPLE HOSTAGE.
IT SEEMS EVERYONE IS AFTER
THESE POOR DELUDED CHILDREN.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Man: HA HA HA!
SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR LITTLE FIELD TRIP,
BUT YOU HAVE SOMETHING
I WANT.
Veemon: DAEMON. THIS SPOOKY
DIGIMON NOT ONLY ATTACKS
WITH HIS GIGANTIC WINGS
AND DEADLY FORCE BEAMS,
BUT HIS EVIL INFERNO
CAN REALLY TURN UP THE HEAT
ON HIS ENEMIES.
OH, CAN'T TOUCH HIM! HOT!
[ Thinking ] MAN,
THIS GUY'S SCARIER
THAN MY GREAT AUNT MARTHA.
I DEMAND YOU GIVE IT TO ME.
FIRST, I MUST SAY
THAT IT'S TRULY AN HONOR
TO SEE YOU IN PERSON,
AND I WOULD LOVE
TO HELP YOU FIND
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR,
BUT I'M AFRAID I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
DON'T TREAT ME LIKE A FOOL.
I KNOW THAT YOU HAVE
THE DARK SPORE.
NOW GIVE IT TO ME WILLINGLY,
OR I WILL TAKE IT.
HMMF.
DAVIS, WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS THE DARK SPORE?
BEATS ME.
BUT WHATEVER IT IS,
I BET IT ISN'T GOOD,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
OH, KEN.
T.K.: I RECEIVED
AN URGENT E-MAIL FROM DAVIS.
HE'S COME ACROSS SOMETHING BIG
IN HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE.
HE NEEDS OUR HELP.
JIM, WE NEED TO GO BACK
TO HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE.
SURE THING, T.K.
BETTER FASTEN
YOUR SEAT BELTS.
Jim: I'M GETTING THE HANG
OF THIS.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
WHY? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T WANT TO KILL
ANOTHER DIGIMON.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT DAVIS
AND KEN ARE IN DANGER RIGHT NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT THEM
TO GET HURT, DO YOU?
NO, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE
ANY MORE DIGIMON GET KILLED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
DON'T WORRY, CODY, WE KNOW
HOW TO TAKE CARE OF OURSELVES.
WE'LL DO OUR BEST
TO MAKE SURE NO ONE GETS HURT.
THANKS, GUYS.
Jim: HOLD ON!
All: WHOA!
HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE LOOKS
SO BEAUTIFUL FROM UP HERE.
IT'S GORGEOUS.
WHEN I WORKED FOR MYOTISMON,
THIS WAS THE FIRST PLACE
ON EARTH I SAW.
HEY, YOU GUYS,
I JUST RECEIVED
AN URGENT E-MAIL
FROM DAVIS.
IT LOOKS LIKE
HE MIGHT'VE FOUND KEN.
T.K. AND CODY ARE ALREADY
ON THEIR WAY,
SO WE BETTER HURRY UP.
GOTCHA. HEAR THAT, AQUILAMON?
WE'VE GOT TO GO.
I'M TWO STEPS
AHEAD OF YOU.
NOW, HANG ON TIGHT.
RIGHT ON.
HANG IN THERE, DAVIS.
[ Thinking ] KNOWING DAVIS,
HE'S IN OVER HIS HEAD AGAIN.
I HOPE
WE'RE NOT TOO LATE.
FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELTS.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A BUMPY RIDE.
I AM GROWING IMPATIENT,
OWIKAWA.
EITHER YOU GIVE ME THE CHILD
WITH THE DARK SPORE NOW,
OR YOU'LL REGRET IT.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO THREATEN ME, DAEMON.
I'M SURE WE CAN WORK THIS OUT
TO OUR MUTUAL SATISFACTION.
[ Thinking ] I'M
CONSISTENTLY AMAZED
AT WHAT FOOLS
THESE DIGIMON CAN BE.
ONCE I GET THE DARK SPORE
PLANTED IN THE OTHERS,
LITTLE ICHIJOUJI
IS EXPENDABLE.
YOU HAVE A SECRET ADMIRER.
VEE HEAD BUTT!
STICKY NET!
OH!
COME ON, KEN.
GO!
VEEMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
X-VEEMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WORMMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
STINGMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
KIDNAPPING, OWIKAWA?
I'M IMPRESSED.
NOW!
KEN, NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
YOU BETTER MAKE A RUN
FOR IT.
NO WAY! I CAN'T LEAVE
UNTIL WE SAVE
THE OTHER CHILDREN.
Davis: OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
OTHER CHILDREN --
WELL, WELL, WELL.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
I HAVE A SURPRISE.
YOU MUST BE KIDDING ME.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
X-VEEMON...
STINGMON...
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
PAILDRAMON!
DESPERADO BLASTER!
TAKE THAT,
WHY DON'T YOU?
NICE SHOOTING, PAILDRAMON.
HA HA HA HA! IS THAT
THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
THAT TICKLED.
KACHINA BOMB!
[ GROANS ]
IT'S SHAKKOUMON!
PERFECT TIMING.
SURELY YOU DON'T EXPECT
THAT OVERGROWN VACUUM CLEANER
TO DEFEAT ME.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'D LIKE TO DO
NOW THAT MY BACK
ISN'T TURNED?
DON'T BACK DOWN, SHAKKOUMON.
HE'S JUST TRYING
TO PSYCH YOU OUT!
YEAH, STAY FOCUSED
AND LET HIM HAVE IT!
HE'S HAD IT NOW.
ASTRO LASER!
IT'S SILPHYMON!
SORRY WE'RE LATE, GUYS.
TAKE THAT, YOU BIG CREEP!
YOU SILLY LITTLE IMBECILES.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOUR PUNY POWERS
ARE ANY MATCH FOR MINE?
EVIL INFERNO!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PAILDRAMON MEGA-DIGIVOLVE TO...
IMPERIALDRAMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
POSITRON LASER!
JUSTICE BEAM!
STATIC FORCE!
BULL'S EYE, BABY!
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
DON'T TELL ME THAT WAS
THE BEST YOU CAN DO.
AH, DUDE.
HEY, LOOK,
NOT EVEN A WRINKLE.
AW, HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO STOP THIS CREEP
IF HE TOOK OUR BEST SHOT?
HA HA HA! NOW IT'S MY TURN
TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN.
Man: GOOD EVENING,
AND WELCOME TO THE 6:00 NEWS.
IN OUR TOP STORY, MONSTER
SIGHTINGS HAVE BEEN REPORTED
FROM THE CITIES OF GINZA
AND TAKASHIBA.
OBVIOUSLY THERE ARE
SOME CRAZY PEOPLE OUT THERE.
WE STILL URGE YOU
TO STAY INDOORS.
THIS JUST IN --
MONSTER ACTIVITY HAS SPREAD
TO HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE.
Woman: WE SHOULD
CALL THE POLICE.
WHAT IF KEN IS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS MONSTER NONSENSE?
KEN'S BRIGHT. IF THERE ARE
MONSTERS AROUND,
I'M SURE HE'S SMART ENOUGH
TO STAY MILES AWAY.
YEAH, MAYBE I'M
OVERREACTING A BIT,
BUT WITH ALL THE RECENT
KIDNAPPINGS IN THE AREA,
I JUST WORRY ABOUT HIM.
LOOK, YOU HAVE
TO CALM DOWN.
KEN IS PROBABLY
ON HIS WAY HOME RIGHT NOW.
I BET HE TOOK THE BUS
AND GOT STUCK IN TRAFFIC
BECAUSE OF ALL
THIS MONSTER BUSINESS.
BUT IF HE'S
DISAPPEARED AGAIN,
I WON'T BE ABLE
TO HANDLE IT.
HONEY...
[ Thinking ] KEN,
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M TRYING TO BE STRONG
FOR YOUR MOTHER,
BUT I'M WORRIED, TOO.
HUH?
IN HEALTH-RELATED NEWS,
THEY FOUND A CURE
FOR THE MONKEY FLU.
MAKE IT EASY ON YOURSELVES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SUFFER.
JUST GIVE ME WHAT I WANT.
COME WITH ME, KEN.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
NO WAY!
MAYBE I CAN PERSUADE YOU
ANOTHER WAY. HA HA HA!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
DO SOMETHING!
HA HA HA!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
IMPERIALDRAMON MODE CHANGE TO...
FIRE MODE!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGIMON ♪
AAH!
WE'RE TOAST!
Both: WHOA!
Cody: LOOK, DAVIS AND KEN ARE
IN SOME SORT OF FORCE FIELD.
WHEN YOU MESS
WITH MY FRIENDS,
I TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
HOW ABOUT A HOT PUNCH?
NOT BAD, FOOL.
I MUST ADMIT, I'M IMPRESSED.
I CAN'T KEEP THIS UP
MUCH LONGER.
HE'S TOO STRONG.
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
I'M GROWING IMPATIENT
WITH THESE LITTLE GAMES.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GIVE UP?
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS,
YOU BIG WINDBAG!
NO WAY!
THIS MONSTER DOESN'T CARE
WHO HE HURTS.
WE CAN'T LET HIM
GET WHAT HE WANTS.
DO YOU HEAR ME,
YOU OVERGROWN PIGEON?
WE'LL NEVER SURRENDER
TO YOU, NO MATTER WHAT.
THIS GUY'S TOO STRONG
TO FIGHT ONE-ON-ONE,
AND WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
TO SEND HIM BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I KNOW! I SAW A LAPTOP
IN JIM'S CAR.
WE CAN OPEN A DIGITAL GATE
FROM THERE
AND SEND HIM BACK.
THAT'LL STOP HIM.
Daemon: YOU WANT TO OPEN
A DIGITAL GATE, DO YOU?
HERE, LET ME HELP YOU!
Davis: HEY, WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS HE DOING?
Kari: IT'S IMPOSSIBLE --
HE'S RIPPING THE SKY APART.
LOOK, HE'S OPENED UP
A DIGITAL GATE ON HIS OWN.
FOOLS! HOW Do YOU THINK
I CAME
FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
GO AHEAD, SEND ME BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I'LL KEEP COMING BACK UNTIL
I GET WHAT I'VE COME FOR!
FACE IT --
YOU CANNOT DEFEAT ME.
NOW COME WITH ME, KEN,
AND MAYBE I'LL GO EASY
ON YOUR FRIENDS.
HE'S RIGHT, IT'S NO USE.
WE'RE FINISHED.
HEY, DON'T YOU TALK
THAT WAY.
WE'RE NOT BEAT YET.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
TO TAKE THIS GUY DOWN.
Cody: SHE'S RIGHT.
HE'S JUST TOO POWERFUL.
NOT YOU, TOO, CODY.
BUT IT'S TRUE, DAVIS.
IMPERIALDRAMON, SILPHYMON,
AND SHAKKOUMON
COULDN'T EVEN MAKE
A SCRATCH
WITH THEIR COMBINED POWERS.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO NOW, HUH?
IT'S COMPLETELY HOPELESS.
EVEN IF WE WERE ABLE
TO SEND HIM BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
IT STILL WON'T STOP HIM.
HE CAN COME RIGHT BACK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
SINCE WHEN DID WE BECOME
A BUNCH OF QUITTERS?
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
TO STOP HIM, GUYS.
IF THERE WAS SOME PLACE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
THAT COULD HOLD A BEAM
THAT POWERFUL,
THEN MAYBE WE COULD...
[ Gasps ]
LIKE THE DARK OCEAN.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S THE WEIRD DIMENSION
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
THAT YOU WENT TO, RIGHT?
GREAT IDEA, KARI.
THAT'S THE PERFECT PLACE
TO SEND THIS FIERY FREAK.
THAT'S GREAT, BUT I THINK
WE'RE OVERLOOKING
A SIMPLE PROBLEM
WITH YOUR PLAN, T.K. --
HOW DO WE OPEN A GATE
TO THE DARK OCEAN?
IT'S STRANGE -- WHEN I WENT
TO THE DARK OCEAN,
I WAS JUST TAKEN THERE
BY SOME MYSTERIOUS FORCE.
I DON'T REMEMBER GOING
THROUGH A PORTAL OR ANYTHING.
WAIT, YOU MEAN
YOU DIDN'T OPEN
THE DIGITAL GATES YOURSELF?
THAT MEANS IT WON'T WORK.
Kari: OH, COME ON, GUYS,
WE'RE ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP NOW.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME WAY
TO SEND HIM
TO THE DARK OCEAN.
HA HA HA! THIS IS BETTER
THAN THE CIRCUS.
PLEASE KEEP COMING UP
WITH THESE FOOLISH PLANS.
YOU'RE MAKING
MY STOMACH HURT.
PUT A SOCK IN IT,
WOULD YOU?
WAIT...
I WAS ONCE ABLE TO OPEN UP
A GATE TO THAT DIMENSION,
USING MY D-3...
A DARK GATE.
[ ALL GASP ]
THERE'S A CHANCE THAT,
EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR ANYMORE,
I STILL MIGHT BE ABLE
TO TAP INTO THAT DARK POWER
TO OPEN UP A PORTAL.
HERE GOES NOTHING!
All: WHOA!
A MAGIC TRICK --
HOW ADORABLE.
LOOK, GUYS!
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING
TO THE DIGITAL GATE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
AAH!
PLEASE, KEN,
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP!
WE'RE RIGHT HERE
WITH YOU.
Davis: CHECK IT OUT --
YOU CAN SEE THE WAVES.
COME ON, GUYS.
THE DARK OCEAN.
IT'S WORKING.
YOU CAN DO IT, KEN!
I BELIEVE IN YOU!
IT'S WORKING.
KEN'S FACING
HIS DARKEST FEARS
AND MAKING IT OPEN.
IF KEN IS BRAVE ENOUGH
TO FIGHT HIS DEMONS,
THEN MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T
GIVE UP SO EASILY.
YEAH, LET'S DO IT.
COME ON, CODY!
HOLD ON.
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS,
AND WE WON'T LET
ANYTHING HAPPEN TO YOU.
CONCENTRATE, KEN.
WE KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
STAY STRONG, KEN.
I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT
OF PAIN AND CONFUSION
INSIDE OF YOU
OVER THE THINGS YOU DID
AS THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
BUT YOU'RE NOT
THAT PERSON ANYMORE, KEN.
YOU THOUGHT THE DIGITAL WORLD
WAS A GAME.
YOU DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE
HURTING LIVING CREATURES.
BUT YOU PAID
FOR YOUR MISTAKES.
WE WOULDN'T BE
WHERE WE ARE
WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
YOU CAN'T KEEP
BEATING YOURSELF UP
FOR ALL THE THINGS
YOU DID IN THE PAST, KEN.
[ Thinking ] WOW, I'VE NEVER
HEARD DAVIS MAKE
THIS MUCH SENSE BEFORE.
[ Thinking ]
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
I THINK I CAN FEEL
KEN LETTING GO OF HIS FEAR.
YOU GOT TO FIGHT, KEN.
YOU'RE STRONGER THAN THAT.
DON'T LET FEAR AND GUILT
RULE YOUR LIFE ANYMORE.
WE'RE HERE WITH YOU.
WHAT A TOUCHING DISPLAY
OF FRIENDSHIP.
I THINK I'M GOING TO CRY.
I THINK I'M GOING
TO DESTROY YOU!
LET'S GET HIM, GUYS.
POSITRON LASER.
STATIC FORCE!
JUSTICE BEAM!
GRRAAH!
FROM THE DARK OCEAN --
VERY IMPRESSIVE,
MY LITTLE DIGIDESTINED.
REMIND ME NOT TO TAKE
YOU SO LIGHTLY NEXT TIME.
YOU MAY THINK
YOU'VE SEEN THE LAST OF ME,
BUT I WILL BE BACK!
HA HA HA HA!
HMMF, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THOSE LITTLE WHELPS
ACTUALLY BEAT DAEMON.
WELL, CALL ME A FOOL.
YEAH!
HA HA HA!
[ Giggling ] YEAH!
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
OWIKAWA -- HE WAS JUST HERE.
WHERE DID HE GO?
CHILDREN,
LISTEN TO ME CLOSELY.
REMEMBER THIS PLACE.
ONE DAY I WILL CALL
YOU ALL BACK HERE.
[ SIRENS BLARING ]
REMEMBER WHAT I TOLD YOU.
HA HA HA!
OWIKAWA!
HURRY. WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
HE'S GETTING AWAY.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS ALL
GOING QUITE WELL.
EVERYTHING'S UNDER CONTROL.
HOW ABOUT A NICE
BIG DOUGHNUT?
IT LOOKS LIKE THE POLICE
WILL MAKE SURE
ALL THOSE CHILDREN
GET HOME OKAY.
YEAH.
I BETTER GET
YOU GUYS HOME.
YOUR PARENTS MUST BE
IN A PANIC BY NOW.
BUT THERE'S ONE PROBLEM --
I ONLY HAVE ROOM
FOR ONE MORE.
WELL, MAYBE I SHOULD GO
TAKE THE BUS, THEN.
GO AHEAD. GO ON.
YOU'RE A PART OF THE TEAM
NOW, KEN.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU, T.K.?
MY PARENTS KNOW
ALL ABOUT THE DIGIMON STUFF.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MY HOUSE ISN'T VERY FAR
FROM HERE.
I'LL JUST WALK HOME.
SEE YOU LATER.
THANKS, BUDDY.
THE DARK SPORE IS IN
ALL THOSE KIDS.
NOW THAT THEY'RE GOING HOME,
WON'T THEIR PARENTS KNOW
THERE'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT
ABOUT THEM
BECAUSE THEY'RE IMPLANTED
WITH THE DARK SPORES?
I DOUBT IT, KARI.
THE CHANGES THEY'LL GO
THROUGH ARE REALLY SUBTLE.
THE TRANSFORMATION WILL BE
SLOW AT FIRST.
THEY'LL START DOING BETTER
IN SCHOOL AND SPORTS.
THAT'S THE FIRST SIGN
THAT THE DARK SPORE
IS GROWING.
YOU DON'T THINK THEY'LL ALL
BECOME DIGIMON EMPERORS ONE DAY,
DO YOU, KEN?
I HOPE NOT.
Man: WELCOME TO THE 10:00 NEWS.
OUR TOP STORY --
POLICE HAVE CRACKED THE CASE
OF THE KIDNAPPED CHILDREN,
RETURNING ALL THE KIDS
TO THEIR WORRIED PARENTS.
KEN STILL ISN'T HOME.
SOMETHING HORRIBLE
HAS HAPPENED. I KNOW IT.
I'LL CALL THE POLICE
AND SEE IF I CAN GET
SOME ANSWERS.
KEN, IS THAT YOU?
YEAH, IT'S ME.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'VE BEEN WORRIED SICK
ABOUT YOU.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO MAKE YOU WORRY.
KEN, I THINK YOU HAVE
A LOT OF EXPLAINING TO DO,
YOUNG MAN.
I'M SORRY, DAD.
WELL, IT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, SON.
WE'RE JUST GLAD
YOU'RE HOME SAFE.
AND IN OTHER NEWS --
MONSTER ACTIVITY
THROUGHOUT THE CITY
HAS MYSTERIOUSLY VANISHED.
I'M REALLY SORRY
WE'RE LATE, MRS. INOUE.
WELL, THANK YOU
FOR BRINGING CODY HOME, JIM.
GOOD NIGHT.
Jim: SO, BY THE TIME
WE FIXED THE FLAT TIRE,
IT WAS WAY PAST DAVIS' CURFEW.
PLEASE DON'T PUNISH DAVIS
FOR GETTING HOME SO LATE.
WELL, I STILL WISH
YOU HAD CALLED,
BUT THANKS FOR GETTING
MY SON HOME SAFELY.
THANK YOU, MA'AM.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD NIGHT, JIM.
DRIVE CAREFULLY.
Davis: TAKE IT EASY, JIM.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
HEY, TELL JOE I SAID HI.
June: DAVIS,
WHO WAS THAT GUY?
THAT'S JOE'S BROTHER.
DOES HE HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND?
WAIT A SECOND.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
IN LOVE WITH MATT.
YOU WOULDN'T STOP BUGGING ME
ABOUT HIM, JUNE.
MATT'S HISTORY.
HUH?
I-I SAW HIM
WITH ANOTHER WOMAN!
IT WAS AT MATT'S CONCERT
WHEN THAT BIG DISGUSTING MONSTER
BURST INTO THE AUDITORIUM.
IN ALL THE CHAOS,
I WAS WAITING FOR MATT
TO SAVE ME, BUT INSTEAD
HE WENT RIGHT TO HER --
SORA.
I KNEW IT WAS OVER THEN.
BUT NOW
I'M A BRAND-NEW WOMAN.
YOUNGER MEN ARE
TOO MUCH TROUBLE.
I NEED SOMEONE
MORE MATURE.
"MRS. JUNE KIDO."
I LIKE THE WAY THAT SOUNDS.
I FEEL SORRY FOR JIM.
LIKE I WAS TELLING YOU,
THE DIGITAL WORLD IS FILLED
WITH DIFFERENT CREATURES
WITH AMAZING POWERS.
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT I HAVE SOMEONE
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET.
MOM AND DAD,
THIS IS WORMMON, MY BEST FRIEND.
GOOD EVENING.
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU.
KEN HAS TOLD ME SO MANY
WONDERFUL THINGS ABOUT YOU.
OH, HONEY,
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HOME.
I THOUGHT I LOST YOU.
DON'T CRY, MOM.
I'M FINE.
Officer: WE DIDN'T CATCH
THE GUY WHO KIDNAPPED THEM.
HE'S GOT TO BE
LONG GONE BY NOW.
BUT WE STILL WANT YOU
TO BE CAREFUL.
ALL RIGHT, MA'AM?
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO THANK YOU, OFFICER.
EXCELLENT.
WITH THE SPORES IMPLANTED,
WE JUST HAVE TO WAIT.
IN TIME THEY'LL BLOOM
INSIDE THE CHILDREN.
MY PLAN IS WORKING
PERFECTLY.
SOON I WILL BE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO DESTROY THOSE DIGIDESTINED
ONCE AND FOR ALL
AND TAKE MY RIGHTFUL PLACE
AS RULER OF THE DIGITAL WORLD!
HA HA HA HA HA!
WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
BE ABLE TO STOP
OWIKAWA'S EVIL PLAN?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON" -- DIGITAL MONSTERS.