WHAT'S WITH DAVIS
AND HIS GOGGLES?
LUNCHROOM DUTY. YUCK.
I KNOW. THESE OUTFITS
ARE TOTALLY HUMILIATING.
YOU SAID IT.
WE LOOK LIKE A COUPLE
OF SALT AND PEPPER SHAKERS.
OR MAD SCIENTISTS.
MAYBE KEN ISN'T
SUCH A BAD GUY AFTER ALL.
I'M NOT SURE.
HE HELPED US LAST TIME.
[ Thinking ] HE'LL HAVE
TO PROVE IT TO ME.
HE'S DONE
SOME EVIL THINGS.
Boy: HEY, MAN,
I WANT MY LUNCH ALREADY.
[ GRUNTS ]
TECHNICALLY, KEN IS
ONE OF THE DIGIDESTINED.
I WAS THINKING
OF ASKING HIM TO JOIN OUR --
[ Thinking ] I GUESS
THAT'S A NO FROM CODY.
IT WAS JUST AN IDEA.
I THOUGHT HE COULD HELP.
I GUESS SOMEONE HASN'T
HAD THEIR COFFEE THIS MORNING.
[ Thinking ]
KEN ONE OF US? IMPOSSIBLE.
WHEN HE WAS THE EMPEROR,
HE WAS RUTHLESS.
HE MIGHT BE PULLING
ANOTHER TRICK ON US.
Davis: I THINK KEN'S CHANGED.
HE'S NOT EMPEROR ANYMORE.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THOUGHT KEN CHANGED, TOO,
ESPECIALLY
AFTER WORMMON GOT HURT.
IT SEEMED HE REALIZED
DIGIMON HAVE FEELINGS.
BUT AFTER OUR LAST BATTLE,
I'M NOT SO SURE.
HE SEEMED A LOT
LIKE THE OLD KEN.
SPIKING STRIKE!
THE WAY HE ORDERED STINGMON
TO GO IN FOR THE KILL --
THE POOR DIGIMON.
IT WAS JUST HORRIBLE.
I'M SORRY, BUT I DON'T
THINK I CAN TRUST HIM.
NO ONE EVER BELIEVES ME.
I'LL JUST HAVE
TO DO THIS ON MY OWN.
DAVIS, WAIT FOR ME.
HEY, DAVIS, WHAT'S UP?
WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK HE'S MAD AT ME
FOR DISAGREEING ABOUT KEN.
HE WANTS TO ASK KEN
TO JOIN US,
EVEN AFTER SEEING THE WAY
HE TREATED THAT DIGIMON.
DAVIS NEEDS TO REALIZE
PEOPLE DON'T CHANGE EASILY.
I'M NOT SO SURE
DAVIS IS WRONG.
MAYBE WE'RE BEING
TOO HARD ON HIM.
WE HAVE MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO WORRY ABOUT,
LIKE WHY THE CONTROL SPIRES
STARTED WORKING AGAIN.
YEAH, LIKE THE SPIRE
AT PRIMARY VILLAGE.
YOU'RE ALWAYS FIRST
TO COMPLETE THE TEST.
I'LL BE FASTER
NEXT TIME.
Boy: LOOK, I BEAT KEN
ON THE MATH TEST!
Girl: ALMOST EVERYONE
BEAT HIM!
Girl #2: WHAT HAPPENED?
HE USED TO BE TOPS.
Boy: MAYBE HIS BRAIN
IS POSSESSED BY AN ALIEN.
Girl #3: IT'S LIKE
HE'S GIVEN UP.
Ken: THEY'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE GIVEN UP.
I CAN'T FOCUS ANYMORE.
I'VE GOT A LOT ON MY MIND.
KEN!
HEY!
SO WHAT BRINGS YOU
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
DID YOU COME TO REMIND ME
I'VE BEEN A BAD BOY?
COME ON, KEN.
YOU'RE NOT AN EVIL PERSON.
I'M NOT?
NO. THE PERSON THAT
DESIGNED THE SCHOOL'S MENU,
NOW THAT'S AN EVIL PERSON.
THAT WAS A JOKE, KEN.
I HAVEN'T BEEN
IN A LAUGHING MOOD LATELY.
THAT'S OKAY.
LOOK, I HAVE AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME?
YOU CAN MEET MY FRIENDS
AND TELL THEM YOU'RE SORRY.
WHY? THEY HATE ME.
THEY JUST
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I KNOW YOU'RE SORRY,
BUT THEY DON'T.
WHAT MAKES YOU
SO SPECIAL?
I JUST
THINK YOU'RE BETTER
THAN YOU'RE GIVING
YOURSELF CREDIT FOR.
THE DIGITAL WORLD'S
BEEN PRETTY FREAKY LATELY.
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
AFTER ALL, YOU'RE ONE
OF US DIGIDESTINED.
HUH? ME, A DIGIDESTINED?
THAT'S RIGHT.
JUST ONE BIG, HAPPY FAMILY.
I DON'T KNOW.
THANKS, DAVIS.
I APPRECIATE YOU
BEING HONEST WITH ME,
BUT IT JUST WON'T WORK.
I CAN'T JOIN YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST CAN'T. SORRY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
COME ON, KEN,
WE COULD BE YOUR FRIENDS.
PLEASE DON'T
TURN YOUR BACK ON US!
I REALLY THOUGHT YOU WERE
GETTING THROUGH TO HIM.
WHY DO YOU THINK HE
DIDN'T WANT TO JOIN US?
I THINK HE
JUST NEEDS TIME,
WHICH WE DON'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF.
HEY, T.K., DO YOU THINK
DAVIS IS RIGHT ABOUT KEN?
SHOULD WE FORGIVE HIM?
EVERYONE DESERVES
A SECOND CHANCE, EVEN KEN.
I BELIEVE HE'S SORRY
FOR WHAT HE'S DONE,
AND IT'S TIME WE LET
BYGONES BE BYGONES.
I HOPE
HE FORGIVES HIMSELF.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID,
AND THE ANSWER
IS STILL NO.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
[ SIGHS ]
HEY, YOLEI,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
HUH?
I'LL BET IT'S SOMETHING
TO DO WITH A BOY.
WELL, KIND OF.
LET ME GUESS.
THIS BOY'S BEEN A REAL JERK
AND YOU WONDER
IF YOU SHOULD FORGIVE HIM.
YES, EXACTLY.
YOU SHOULD GIVE HIM
ANOTHER CHANCE.
AFTER ALL,
HE IS YOUR BOYFRIEND.
HMM?
ACCORDING
TO GIRLIE-GIRL MAGAZINE,
YOUR HOROSCOPE SAYS YOU'RE
GOING TO BE LUCKY IN LOVE.
WAIT A SECOND.
YOU GUYS HAVE IT ALL WRONG.
I DON'T HAVE
A BOYFRIEND, GOT IT?
YEP, THAT'S WHAT
THEY ALL SAY.
AH, YOUNG LOVE -- SWEET.
HMM. NOW I'M
REALLY CONFUSED.
MAYBE DAVIS IS RIGHT
ABOUT KEN.
IF THIS IS BOTHERING YOU
SO MUCH,
WHY DON'T YOU TALK
TO KEN YOURSELF?
I KNOW THAT'S
THE RIGHT THING TO DO,
BUT THIS LITTLE VOICE
KEEPS TELLING ME
KEN IS STILL UNTRUSTWORTHY.
LISTENING TO LITTLE VOICES
SOUNDS PRETTY WEIRD TO ME.
AH!
RATS!
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
I JUST HOPE I CAN
MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION.
[ GROWLING ]
NOW, STINGMON!
GO GET HIM!
TWIN SICKLES!
MAYBE IF YOU
PRACTICED MORE.
SPINNING, SPIKING STRIKE!
STINGMON -- THIS INSECTOID
DIGIMON BUGS OPPONENTS
WITH HIS SPIKING STRIKE ATTACK.
DON'T TRY BUG SPRAY
ON HIM, THOUGH.
IT'LL ONLY MAKE HIM ANGRY.
SPIKING STRIKE!
HE'S GONE TO PIECES.
YOU SHOWED HIM, STINGMON.
CAN WE NOT DO THAT
ANYMORE TODAY, KEN?
UNFORTUNATELY,
I DON'T THINK
THAT WAS THE LAST
OF THE MONSTERS WE'LL FACE.
LOOK AT ALL
THESE CONTROL SPIRES.
I'M SORRY
I EVER MADE THEM.
MAYBE I SHOULD JOIN
THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED.
I DON'T THINK
WE CAN DO THIS ALONE.
Girl: I WANT
A MARSHMALLOW, MIMI.
HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
PALMON IS BRINGING BACK
MORE MARSHMALLOWS RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS GREAT. THANK YOU.
YOU YUKIMIBOTAMON
ARE CUTE BABY DIGIMON.
YOUR BUBBLE BLOW ATTACK
IS ALMOST AS BIG
AS YOUR APPETITES.
NEXT TIME WE'LL MAKE SMORES.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
I WONDER
WHERE PALMON WENT TO.
IF SHE DOESN'T HURRY,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO START ROASTING TREE BARK.
OH, HOW PRETTY.
I BET MIMI
WILL LOVE THIS FLOWER.
I SHOULD FIND MORE
AND MAKE HER A BOUQUET.
[ HUMMING ]
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
A HUMAN.
BUT WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT ONLY CHILDREN
COULD COME
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
SHE DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A CHILD TO ME.
AND WHAT'S SHE DOING
WITH THAT CONTROL SPIRE?
[ CHUCKLES ]
"HAIR" TODAY, GONE TOMORROW.
SPIRIT NEEDLE!
HMM.
[ GASPS ]
OHH!
OH, THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
[ MONSTER GROWLS ]
GO, FLOOD THE CITY.
LEAVE IT IN RUINS.
NOW DO AS I COMMAND.
[ GROWLS ]
OH, NO!
MIMI! MIMI, HELP!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
MIMI, HELP! YOU HAVE
TO MAKE ME DIGIVOLVE.
HE'S GOING TO DESTROY
THE WHOLE TOWN.
PALMON, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WHO'S GOING
TO DESTROY THE TOWN?
OHH!
[ ROARS ]
PALMON!
Yukimibotamon: IT'S GOLEMON!
GOLEMON, A MONSTROUS DIGIMON
MADE OF STONE AND MINERALS.
HIS CRIMSON CURSE ATTACK
OVERPOWERS HIS ENEMIES.
THAT WAS TOO CLOSE.
[ GOLEMON ROARS ]
PALMON!
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M ALL RIGHT.
I JUST NEED TO REST.
GO, MIMI. GOLEMON'S GOING
TO DESTROY THE DAM.
OHH!
GOLEMON, WAIT! STOP!
DON'T DO IT!
STOP! THE TOWN IS DEFENSELESS,
YOU BIG BULLY!
THERE'S NO TIME.
YOU MUST WARN THEM,
AND I NEED TO SLEEP.
PALMON, HOLD ON.
OHH!
I CAN'T DO THIS ALONE.
I NEED HELP.
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
Davis: DIGIPORT OPEN.
Yolei: MIMI,
WE'RE RIGHT HERE.
Davis: WE CAME
AS FAST AS WE COULD.
ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S GOLEMON.
HE'S GOING TO DESTROY
THE DAM AND FLOOD THE CITY.
DID HE JUST FREAK OUT
OR SOMETHING?
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
WHERE'S THE TOWN?
AT THE END OF THE RAVINE.
ALL THE DIGIMON DOWN THERE
WILL BE UP TO THEIR
DIGI-EARS IN WATER.
HEY, DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE ALL OVER IT.
LET'S TAKE CARE
OF THAT ROCK-HEAD.
All: YEAH!
FIRST WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO GET HIM OFF THAT DAM.
Both: GOLDEN NOOSE!
HUH?
IT'S MY TURN.
THUNDER BLAST!
GOLD RUSH!
DOUBLE STARS!
GREAT SHOT, GUYS.
Both: HUH?
AAH!
OUR SHOTS
DIDN'T EVEN FAZE HIM.
HE'S TOO STRONG.
LOOK FOR HIS DARK RING
AND DESTROY IT.
I'M ALL OVER IT.
I DON'T SEE A DARK RING.
NO DARK RING? THAT MEANS
HE'S NOT BEING CONTROLLED.
YEAH, JUST LIKE THAT
THUNDERMON I FOUGHT LAST TIME.
[ ROARS ]
AAH!
[ ALL GASP ]
PEGASUSMON!
AAH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT DID IT.
AAH!
CRIMSON CURSE!
[ COUGHING ]
HEY, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
MY TURN.
AAH!
DOUBLE STARS!
SHURIMON!
LOOK, HE'S GOING TO DO IT.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
THERE ARE MILLIONS
OF GALLONS
POURING OUT OF THAT HOLE.
WE HAVE TO STOP IT.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
Yukimibotamon:
OH, NO, THE TOWN!
QUICK, YOU GUYS,
STOP THE WATER!
YOU HEARD THE LADY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
ROSETTA STONE!
AAH!
TAKE THAT,
YOU BIG ROCK-HEAD.
UNH!
AAH!
SORRY, BUT I'VE ALREADY
HAD MY BATH TODAY.
AAH!
DOUBLE STARS!
THUNDER BLAST!
GOLDEN NOOSE!
ROCK CRACKING!
GOING UP?
THERE MUST BE EASIER WAYS
TO WATER THE PLANTS.
YOU'RE TELLING ME.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL TEAMWORK.
All: OH, NO,
GOLEMON'S AT IT AGAIN!
HE'S CLIMBING
THE DAM AGAIN.
DOESN'T HE KNOW
WHEN TO STOP?
I DON'T THINK SO.
HE HAS A ROCK FOR A BRAIN.
HE CAN'T BE THAT BRIGHT.
THERE'S NO WAY THE DIGIMON
CAN STOP THAT MUCH WATER.
LET'S GO.
WHY IS HE SO INTENT
ON FLOODING THE TOWN?
GOLEMON DOESN'T CARE
THERE ARE DIGIMON DOWN THERE.
THAT'S WHY WE
HAVE TO STOP HIM.
THOSE POOR DIGIMON.
HOW DO WE STOP GOLEMON
WITHOUT HURTING HIM?
Davis: WE HAVE TO RESORT
TO EXTREME MEASURES.
AND EXACTLY WHAT
DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
WE HAVE TO DESTROY HIM.
HAVE YOU GONE
COMPLETELY NUTS?
HE'S A DIGIMON,
A LIVING CREATURE.
THINK OF ANOTHER PLAN.
IF YOU'VE GOT A BETTER PLAN,
I'D LOVE TO HEAR IT.
LET'S GET HIM.
WHAT IF WE KEEP TRYING
TO PROTECT THE DAM?
HE SWATTED
OUR DIGIMON LIKE FLIES.
WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT GOLEMON
TO PROTECT THE DAM.
AT LEAST LET'S TRY,
DAVIS.
THE LONGER WE FIGHT HIM,
THE BETTER THE CHANCE
OF HIM DESTROYING THAT DAM.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A BETTER WAY.
IT'S TOO LATE, YOLEI.
WE HAVE TO ACT NOW.
IF WE DESTROY GOLEMON,
WE'RE NO BETTER
THAN KEN AND STINGMON.
I AGREE WITH YOLEI.
IF WE DESTROY GOLEMON,
WE'LL JUST BE SINKING
TO KEN'S LEVEL.
RIGHT, CODY.
WRONG, CODY. WE HAVE
TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
BEING A HERO
ISN'T ALWAYS PRETTY.
MAYBE KEN DID WHAT HE HAD TO
TO SAVE PEOPLE'S LIVES.
WHY DOES DAVIS
ALWAYS STICK UP FOR KEN,
EVEN AFTER HE'S SEEN HIM
DO SUCH HORRIBLE THINGS?
DOES HE REALLY THINK
KEN HAS CHANGED?
THIS MIGHT SOUND CRAZY,
BUT I THINK WE SHOULD
ASK KEN FOR HIS HELP.
HAVE YOU LOST
YOUR MIND, MIMI?
GIVE ME YOUR D-3.
YOU HAVE GOT
TO BE KIDDING.
I'M TOTALLY SERIOUS.
GOLEMON'S TOO POWERFUL.
WE NEED ALL THE HELP
WE CAN GET.
DON'T ARGUE WITH ME.
MIMI, HOW DO YOU KNOW
IF WE CAN TRUST HIM?
MAYBE I AM BEING
TOO HARD ON KEN.
I REALLY DO WANT HIM TO COME,
I JUST CAN'T ADMIT IT.
AAH!
UNH!
OHH.
HAWKMON, NO!
OHH!
READY, GUYS?
CRIMSON CURSE!
[ ALL COUGHING ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ROARS ]
RUN FOR IT! HE'S GOING
TO BREAK THE DAM!
HUH?
IT'S STINGMON!
[ PANTING ]
STINGMON,
GIVE HIM YOUR BEST SHOT.
HERE GOES NOTHING.
IT'S KEN.
HE CAME TO HELP US.
WAY TO GO! YEAH!
I KNEW HE'D COME!
ME, TOO.
NOW GOLEMON
HAS HIS HANDS FULL.
[ YOLEI GULPS ]
WOW. KEN AND STINGMON
ARE DEFENDING THE TOWN.
IF STINGMON
HADN'T STOPPED GOLEMON,
THE DAM WOULD BE
HISTORY BY NOW.
AAH!
UNH!
[ GROANS ]
LOOK, EVERYONE.
PALMON'S WAKING UP.
GOLEMON!
HE'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
[ GROWLING ]
HE'S NOT EVEN
A REAL DIGIMON.
I KNOW I SOUND CRAZY,
BUT YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I WAS WALKING
THROUGH THE WOODS
AND I HEARD SOMETHING.
THAT'S WHEN I SAW
THIS STRANGE WOMAN.
SHE WAS CASTING A SPELL
ON A CONTROL SPIRE.
[ GASPS ]
THERE WAS ALL THIS
BRIGHT LIGHT,
AND THEN THE CONTROL SPIRE
BECAME GOLEMON.
GUYS, I JUST
THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
THUNDERMON MUST HAVE BEEN
ONE OF THOSE SPIRES, TOO.
I BET KEN
FIGURED THAT OUT
DURING THE LAST BATTLE.
THAT MUST BE WHY HE ORDERED
STINGMON TO DESTROY HIM.
HE KNEW HE WASN'T
A REAL DIGIMON.
Cody: GOLEMON,
HE'S UNDER A DARK SPELL.
STINGMON, LOOK OUT!
I WAS WRONG.
KEN HAS CHANGED.
I ASSUMED HE WAS
AS RUTHLESS AS BEFORE,
BUT NOW HE'S TRYING
TO SAVE THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I'M SORRY, KEN.
I WAS WRONG.
[ GASPS ]
OHH.
HAWKMON, ARE YOU OKAY?
I FEEL RATHER STRANGE
RIGHT NOW.
OHH.
I KNEW I WAS WRONG.
HAWKMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
AQUILAMON!
AQUILAMON -- THIS GIANT,
WINGED DIGIMON
SOARS ALONG
AT SUPERSONIC SPEEDS,
AND BEATS HIS OPPONENTS
WITH HIS GRAND HORN ATTACK.
[ GROWLS ]
AQUILAMON!
GOLEMON IS REALLY
AN EVIL CONTROL SPIRE.
HE'S NOT A LIVING DIGIMON,
SO GIVE HIM ALL YOU'VE GOT.
[ ROARS ]
[ GROWLS ]
EXCUSE ME.
BLAST RINGS!
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
STINGMON, ATTACK!
SPIKING STRIKE!
AAH!
OHH!
AQUILAMON, HE'S WEAKENED.
GET HIM.
GRAND HORN!
[ GROANS ]
THEY DID IT.
JUST IN TIME FOR LUNCH.
I WON'T MAKE ANY EXCUSES,
AND I'M SORRY
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE.
All: HMM?
THANKS FOR COMING
WHEN WE CALLED YOU, KEN.
WE WERE NEARLY FINISHED
BACK THERE.
IT'S THE LEAST
I COULD DO.
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT WEIRD WOMAN
WHO TURNS CONTROL SPIRES
INTO DARK DIGIMON.
WORMMON AND I DISCOVERED
SHE IS ABLE TO RECHARGE
THE OLD CONTROL SPIRES
THROUGH DARK MAGIC.
IF YOU KNEW
ABOUT THE CONTROL SPIRES,
WHY DIDN'T
YOU SAY SOMETHING?
WELL, I --
WE MADE THE MESS.
WE WANTED TO CLEAN IT UP.
YOU SHOULD HAVE CALLED
A MAID SERVICE, WORMMON.
I WASN'T SURE IF YOU GUYS
WERE GOING TO BELIEVE ME.
I WOULD HAVE, BUT THE REST
WOULD HAVE BEEN A HARD SELL.
WE NEED TO START OVER.
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN US?
I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T.
WE CAN FIGURE THIS OUT
TOGETHER.
AT LEAST THINK IT OVER.
WE REALLY NEED YOUR HELP.
Ken: HUH?
E-MAIL.
"THANKS FOR HELPING US
TODAY.
"I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE DAY
YOU DECIDE TO JOIN US, KEN.
YOLEI."
Yolei: DON'T WORRY.
I THINK HE'LL COME AROUND.
I DON'T BLAME HIM
FOR BEING CAUTIOUS.
BESIDES, WE CAN ALWAYS USE
ANOTHER DIGIDESTINED.
WILL KEN JOIN THE REST
OF THE DIGIDESTINED?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."