HOLD ON AGUMON
I'LL BE THERE SOON
JUST A FEW MORE MINUTES.
OH! INTEGRATE QUADRATIC...
IT'S LIKE THIS STUFF
MAKES NO SENSE.
[ BELL RINGS ]
Kari: HURRY!
T.K.: WE'RE LATE!
Davis: QUIT SPLASHING!
YOU GUYS ARE LATE.
WE'RE SO SORRY, TAI.
HEY, DON'T BLAME KARI.
IT'S MY FAULT WE'RE LATE.
I HAD AN APPOINTMENT
FOR A HAIRCUT,
BUT I REALIZED
MY HAIR WAS PERFECT.
HE WAS LOOKING
IN THE MIRROR
FOR OVER AN HOUR.
BUT WHAT ABOUT AGUMON?
HAVE HIM
MAKE HIS OWN APPOINTMENT.
DAVIS, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO BE A DIGIDESTINED,
THINK LESS OF YOUR HAIR
AND MORE OF THE TEAM.
NOW LET'S GO
AND SAVE AGUMON.
BUT WHERE IS YOLEI?
SHE'S CLEANING HER GLASSES.
AS BIG AS HER GLASSES ARE,
THAT COULD TAKE HOURS.
WHEN ARE PEOPLE GOING
TO LEARN TO WEAR GOGGLES?
GO FIND HER
SO WE CAN LEAVE ALREADY!
Cody: I'LL GO, TOO.
YOLEI?
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
TO GO TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WE'RE GOING
TO SAVE AGUMON.
AND SHOW THAT DIGITAL
EMPEROR JUST WHO'S BOSS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M NOT GOING.
WHY NOT? TELL US
SO WE CAN HELP.
YOU'RE THE LAST PERSON
I WOULD TURN TO
IF I WAS IN TROUBLE
AND NEEDED SOME HELP.
BE NICE, TAI.
I'M SORRY. I'M WORRIED
ABOUT AGUMON.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO PUT YOURSELF IN DANGER
IF YOU'RE NOT
UP TO THE CHALLENGE.
MAYBE IT WOULD BE BEST
IF YOU STAYED.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE GOING
IF THEIR HEART'S NOT INTO IT.
AND IF IT WILL MAKE YOU FEEL
ANY BETTER, YOLEI,
YOU CAN STAY AND DO MY MATH
HOMEWORK TO KEEP YOURSELF BUSY.
MY KENDO STICKS
COULD USE SOME POLISHING.
IT'S ALL RIGHT
IF I DON'T GO?
SURE. YOU CAN MAKE
A DAY OF IT --
CLEANING, MATH HOMEWORK,
AND ALL THOSE FUN THINGS.
YOU SURE?
IF EVERYONE SAYS
YOU SHOULD STAY,
THEN YOU SHOULD STAY.
GATOMON'S RIGHT, YOLEI.
IF YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE GOING
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
THEN I DON'T FEEL
LIKE GOING EITHER.
NOW THAT THAT'S SETTLED,
LET'S GO GET AGUMON.
RIGHT.
IF EVERYONE'S READY,
LET'S GO, DIGIDESTINED.
DIGIPORT OPEN!
♪ LET'S GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-OH ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-O-OH ♪
THE DARK RINGS KEEP FAILING ME.
FIRST THERE WAS ANDROMON...
AND THEN SKULLGREYMON.
[ GASPS ]
THE DARK RING --
THERE MUST BE A FLAW WITH IT,
BUT WHAT COULD BE WRONG?
IS IT JUST
NOT POWERFUL ENOUGH?
OOH, I CAN STILL EXPERIMENT
ON GREYMON.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE
THE WHOLE GANG BACK.
WELCOME TO MY TREE HOUSE.
IT'S NOT MUCH OF A TREE HOUSE
SINCE SKULLGREYMON
DISINTEGRATED IT.
NOW IT'S MORE
OF A TWIG HOUSE.
THAT'S OKAY. I WAS PLANNING
ON REDECORATING ANYWAY.
WE DON'T CARE ABOUT
YOUR STUPID TREE, TENTOMON.
WE'RE HERE TO STOP
THE DIGITAL EMPEROR
FROM HURTING MORE DIGIMON.
IT'S INCREDIBLY IMPORTANT
WE STOP HIM.
IF HE CONTINUES TO GAIN POWER
LIKE THIS,
HE'LL THREATEN
THE ENTIRE DIGITAL WORLD.
HEY, WATCH IT, CODY.
BE CAREFUL.
I'M SORRY, BUT THAT KEN
MAKES ME SO ANGRY.
YEAH, ME TOO.
ARMADILLOMON, YOU REALLY
NEED TO CONTROL YOUR TEMPER.
HOW ARE WE
GOING TO FIND OUT
WHERE AGUMON IS?
TENTOMON WILL HELP.
NOW THAT TENTOMON IS
OUT OF HIS TREE,
MAYBE WE CAN CLIMB IT
AND LOOK AROUND.
Tentomon: STAY OUT
OF MY TREE!
YOU OKAY?
TAI HASN'T BEEN THIS ANGRY
SINCE I POPPED HIS SOCCER BALL
WITH MY CLAWS.
HE HAS A RIGHT TO BE.
STANDING AROUND IS MAKING
MY PAWS ITCH. LET'S GET GOING.
GOOD IDEA. I'LL GO SEE
WHAT I CAN FIND OUT.
AND DON'T TOUCH MY TREE.
I KNOW EXACTLY HOW MANY
PIECES OF BARK ARE ON IT.
EVERYTHING WILL BE
OKAY, TAI.
I KNOW.
GREYMON,
THE TIME HAS COME.
GREYMON, DARK DIGEVOLVE!
GREYMON,
DARK DIGEVOLVE TO --
SKULLGREYMON!
LOOK, MASTER,
HE'S TRYING TO ESCAPE.
AND WE JUST HAD THOSE WALLS
RE-STUCCOED.
HE'S TOO POWERFUL.
HE'S OVERLOADING
THE DARK RING.
I MUST TRANSFER
MORE POWER TO IT.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
WE CAN'T CONTROL
SKULLGREYMON.
HE'S TOO POWERFUL.
OH, YEAH? WANT TO BET?
PLEASE, MASTER,
LET'S JUST LET HIM GO.
BE QUIET.
GREYMON, DARK DIGEVOLVE!
[ Thinking ] WHY WON'T HE
EVER LISTEN TO ME?
Tai: LOOK, A CONTROL SPIRE.
THIS IS ONE OF THE AREAS
CONTROLLED
BY THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
SOMETHING'S COMING!
CAREFUL, FLAMEDRAMON!
I AM WOODMON.
I CANNOT BE DEFEATED.
FLAME SHIELD!
AAH!
HEY, I'M BEING DEFEATED!
FIRE ROCKET!
YIKES! AAH!
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME,
AND WHO ARE YOU?
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
CAN BE FOUND?
WELL, I'M NOT REALLY SURE,
BUT I THINK
HE WENT THAT WAY.
THANKS A BUNCH.
GO! GO!
WAIT! CAN I GET
A LITTLE HELP HERE?
SERIOUSLY.
BIG SPIRE. REALLY HEAVY.
[ Thinking ]
I CLEANED MY GLASSES
FOR THE THIRD TIME TODAY
AND I'M STILL NOT HAPPY.
WEIRD.
TAI, GUYS,
IS EVERYTHING OKAY? OHH.
THEY PROBABLY DON'T WANT
TO TALK TO ME ANYMORE
AFTER I LET THEM DOWN.
WELL, IT'S TIME I GOT TOUGH.
OOPS, I MISSED A SPOT.
Tentomon: According
to my information,
Agumon can be found
in Rail Town.
THAT'S GREAT, TENTOMON.
I'LL LET THEM KNOW.
And tell them
to stay out of my tree.
UH, YOU BET.
IS EVERYBODY OKAY, IZZY?
TENTOMON MAY HAVE FOUND AGUMON.
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
I WANT TO HELP. PLEASE LET
ME TELL THEM, OKAY?
OH, SURE. JUST TELL THEM
ABOUT RAIL TOWN.
YEAH.
ONCE MORE.
THE POWER LEVELS.
HMM.
FOOLISH CREATURE.
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER
THAN TO FIGHT ME,
BUT YOU'VE GIVEN ME
WHAT I NEED.
THE DARK RING CAN CONTROL
AN ADULT-STAGE DIGIMON
BUT NOT
A FULLY EVOLVED DIGIMON.
IT NEEDS TO BE
A DIFFERENT SHAPE
LIKE A CYLINDER OR A --
[ Gasps ]
OF COURSE. I KNOW
WHAT I NEED TO DO NOW.
HEH HEH HEH HEH HEH.
Cody: TAI, SLOW DOWN.
Tai: WE DON'T HAVE
THE TIME.
OH, HEY, LOOK.
WE'VE MADE IT. RAIL TOWN.
Kari: RAIL TOWN.
Cody: RAIL TOWN.
Davis: LOOKS MORE LIKE
GRASS AND HILL TOWN TO ME.
COME ON, GUYS, AGUMON IS
IN THIS TOWN SOMEWHERE.
SO LET'S GO!
EVERYBODY SPLIT UP
AND START LOOKING FOR HIM.
IF AGUMON ESCAPES,
KEN WILL HAVE TO USE ME,
BUT HE'S GOING TO BE MAD.
I'LL BAKE HIM SOME BROWNIES.
THE DARK RING'S GONE.
I'M FREE!
AH. NOW IT'S TIME
FOR A LITTLE PAYBACK.
THIS NEW STRUCTURE WILL
INCREASE THE POWER TENFOLD.
I WON'T EVEN NEED
THE CONTROL SPIRES.
HA HA HA.
NO ONE WILL EVER BE ABLE
TO STOP ME
FROM TAKING OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD!
NOT A DARK RING,
BUT A DARK SPIRAL!
WITH THIS I CAN CONTROL EVEN
A FULLY DIGEVOLVED DIGIMON.
NOW, TO TEST IT
ON AGUMON.
WHAT? HE'S GONE!
BUT -- BUT HOW?
Davis: TAI, AGUMON'S CLOSE.
I'M FOLLOWING HIS TRACKS.
Tai: THOSE ARE TRAIN TRACKS,
DAVIS.
WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
HUH?
Kari: IT'S EITHER THE LOCAL
OR THE EXPRESS.
AND LOOK WHO'S DRIVING.
WHOA!
OH!
IT'S -- IT'S AGUMON.
AGUMON!
TAI!
Gatomon: THAT OUGHT
TO SLOW HIM DOWN.
AGUMON, ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE. TAI!
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
GIVE ME A GREAT BIG HUG.
OUCH.
ARE YOU OKAY?
DID HE HURT YOU?
NO, YOU WERE JUST
SQUEEZING MY RIBS TOO HARD.
TAI, WE SHOULD GET GOING.
I'M SURE KEN
WILL COME AFTER AGUMON.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
WE ALL CAME HERE TO FIGHT!
NOW YOU WANT US
TO TURN AROUND AND GO HOME?
I WANT TO GET THE GUY
WHO DID THIS TO AGUMON, TOO,
BUT SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO THINK
WITH YOUR HEAD, NOT YOUR HEART.
REMEMBER, WE'RE NOT
AT FULL STRENGTH.
AGUMON'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT,
SO OUR FIRST PRIORITY IS
TO GET HIM BACK TO SAFETY.
YOU MEAN WE CAN COME BACK
HERE LATER AND GET HIM?
MM-HMM.
HOW DID AGUMON GET AWAY?
AN ESCAPE CLAUSE
IN HIS CONTRACT?
I'M IN NO MOOD FOR HUMOR.
GOOD, BECAUSE I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING SERIOUS.
MASTER?
WHAT?
I-I WAS JUST THINKING
THAT YOU COULD USE ME
FOR YOUR EXPERIMENTS.
I MEAN, I AM A DIGIMON
JUST LIKE AGUMON.
I CAN DIGEVOLVE, TOO.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I SAY YOU CAN
FORGET ABOUT IT!
BUT, MASTER, PLEASE.
I'VE DONE ABSOLUTELY
EVERYTHING AROUND HERE
YOU'VE ASKED ME TO DO
AND MORE.
I EVEN CLEANED THAT HAIR TRAP
THING IN THE SHOWER.
HA! AND WHAT KIND OF DIGIMON
WOULD YOU DIGEVOLVE INTO?
PERHAPS
YOU'D TRANSFORM YOURSELF
INTO A GIANT BUTTERFLY
WITH SCARY-LOOKING WINGS?
HA! YOU'RE ABOUT
AS USELESS TO ME
AS AN OLD PAIR OF UNDERWEAR
THAT'S MADE
OF 100% POISON IVY.
GIVE ME A CHANCE, KEN,
AND YOU WON'T BE --
AND WILL YOU STOP
CALLING ME KEN?
MY NAME IS
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR!
ALL I'M SAYING IS NOW
THAT AGUMON HAS ESCAPED,
I'M ALL YOU'VE GOT.
ENOUGH! HUH?
THEY'RE HERE
AND THEY'VE GOT AGUMON.
HE'S A USEFUL DIGIMON.
BUT, KEN, I AM -- OHH!
WE'LL HAVE COOKIES
AND ICE CREAM.
I WANT MINE
WITH CHOCOLATE SPRINKLES.
HOW ENDEARING.
Kari: IT'S KEN.
MY NAME IS
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR!
NOW YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE CALLED KEN, HUH?
HOW'S KENNY OR KENNETH?
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT
TO MAKE ME ANGRY.
SO, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO PUT AGUMON IN A CAGE
LIKE A WILD ANIMAL.
YOU COME DOWN AND TAKE
YOUR MEDICINE LIKE A MAN.
YOU DO AMUSE ME SO.
I CAN DEFEAT YOU JUST
AS I DEFEATED AGUMON.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF, KEN.
YOU'RE THE KIND OF BULLY
THAT GIVES BULLIES
A BAD NAME.
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO DO BETTER THAN THAT,
LITTLE BOY.
Davis: DARK TYRANNOMON!
Tai: WE'RE SURROUNDED!
GIVE ME THE WORD,
DAVIS.
YEAH!
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE.
DON'T LET FLAMEDRAMON
HAVE ALL THE FUN, CODY.
RIGHT.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
FLAMING FIST!
AHH!
♪ SOMETHING MAJOR... ♪
ROCK CRACKING!
♪ NOW I'M IN BETWEEN ♪
THEY'RE WINNING!
FIRE ROCKET!
HE'S TOUGH.
I'LL SAY.
Both: DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
GATOMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
NEFERTIMON,
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PATAMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
PEGASUSMON, FLYING HOPE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ROSETTA STONE!
WIND MANE!
EQUUS BEAM!
ATTACK!
AGUMON!
SO, YOU'VE COME BACK TO ME,
AGUMON,
AND I'VE GOT A NEW
FRIENDSHIP BRACELET FOR YOU.
AAH!
WHAT IS THIS?
AHH!
YOU ARE MINE AGAIN!
[ GROWLS ]
AGUMON,
ARE YOU OKAY?
LOOK OUT!
HE'S BEING CONTROLLED
AGAIN.
NOW, AGUMON,
DARK DIGEVOLVE!
AGUMON
DARK DIGEVOLVE TO...
METALGREYMON!
HE LOOKS SO DIFFERENT.
AND MEAN.
METALGREYMON'S ARMOR NOT ONLY
PROTECTS HIM FROM HARM,
BUT IT CONCEALS HIS DESTRUCTIVE
GIGABLASTER ATTACK.
THE DARK SPIRAL
IS WORKING PERFECTLY.
AGUMON IS MINE AGAIN!
METALGREYMON,
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGHT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
CONTROL.
IT'S ME -- TAI.
DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
OOH, SUCH A TENSE MOMENT.
I'VE GOT CHILLS.
WILL HE REMEMBER YOU?
ALLOW ME TO ANSWER.
METALGREYMON, ATTACK!
LOOK OUT!
TAI, HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHO YOU ARE.
Pegasusmon: NEFERTIMON,
HELP ME STOP METALGREYMON.
Both: GOLDEN NOOSE!
GRAAH!
DON'T HURT HIM.
HE'S METAL.
HE'LL BE FINE.
HEY! WHOA, HOLD IT!
WE'VE GOT HIM TRAPPED.
DIGMON, CAN YOU GET
TO THE DARK SPIRAL?
THAT WON'T BE A PROBLEM
FOR OLD DIGMON
IF HE'D JUST STOP
DANCING AROUND.
HEY, QUIT IT!
Tai: AGUMON!
OKAY,
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
LET GO!
I'M STILL TOO SCARED
TO MOVE.
I'VE FORGOTTEN
HOW TO MOVE.
Pegasusmon: HE'S TRYING
TO BREAK THE GOLDEN NOOSE!
LET ME JUST TRY
TO REACH HIM. AHH!
THE ONLY THING
YOU'LL REACH
IS THE BOTTOM
OF HIS FOOTPRINT, TAI.
[ ROARS ]
AAH!
GIGABLASTER!
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
[ COUGHS ]
WITH THE NEW DARK SPIRALS,
I WILL CONTROL
THE WHOLE DIGITAL WORLD!
GOODBYE, DIGIFOOLS,
AND SAY GOODBYE
TO YOUR PET AGUMON FOR GOOD.
AGUMON, NO!
WITH THE DARK SPIRALS
AND METALGREYMON,
I AM INVINCIBLE!
METALGREYMON
IS THE MISSING LINK I NEEDED.
THERE'S NOTHING
THAT CAN STOP ME NOW.
HA HA HA HA HA!
Davis: THAT KID IS JUST BEGGING
TO BE TAKEN DOWN A PEG.
Cody: BUT HOW CAN WE
DEFEAT HIM?
I LET AGUMON DOWN JUST
WHEN HE NEEDED ME THE MOST,
AND I -- HUH?
T.K.: IT'S YOLEI
AND HAWKMON.
Kari: AND MATT!
I'M SORRY
ABOUT NOT COMING BEFORE.
THAT'S OKAY. I KNEW
YOU'D SHOW UP EVENTUALLY.
IT'S A GOOD THING
SHE DID STAY
OR I NEVER
WOULD HAVE FOUND YOU ALL.
WHY DON'T YOU FILL ME IN
ON WHAT'S HAPPENED
UP UNTIL NOW?
I SEE.
WELL, IT CERTAINLY SOUNDS
LIKE YOU GUYS
HAD A FULL DAY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
TAI...
HEY, WHY ARE YOU
HITTING TAI?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE FRIENDS,
AND FRIENDS
DON'T FIGHT FRIENDS
UNLESS THEY'RE
ON A BOXING TEAM.
T.K.: DAVIS,
LET THEM BE!
TAI?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANKS, MAN.
I NEEDED THAT.
SURE, ANY TIME.
I'LL DO IT AGAIN.
I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
I KNOW THAT I WAS
JUST BLAMING MYSELF
FOR SOMETHING THAT WAS
COMPLETELY OUT OF MY CONTROL.
IT DOESN'T HELP
IF I STAND AROUND HERE
AND FEEL SORRY FOR MYSELF.
NOW WE NEED TO FOCUS ON HOW
WE CAN GET AGUMON BACK.
WE HAVE TO BE WILLING
TO FIGHT AGUMON
AT FULL STRENGTH.
I'M SURE AGUMON
WOULD DEFINITELY RATHER
BE DEFEATED BY US
THAN REMAIN A SLAVE
TO THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IN THE FUTURE,
WHEN WE BATTLE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
WE HAVE TO BE PREPARED TO FACE
OUR FRIEND AGUMON AS WELL.
SO, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
HOW TO SAY THIS...
Gatomon: LET ME
HANDLE THIS, TAI.
THE NEXT TIME YOU SEE AGUMON,
TRASH HIM. UNDERSTAND?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
All: OKAY!
DEFEAT AGUMON!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THOSE WORDS
CAME OUT OF MY MOUTH!
YEAH, LET'S ALL GO
GET AGUMON BACK!
Tai: I'VE NEVER TRAVELED
BY SAILING TRAIN CAR BEFORE.
Kari: THAT'S HOW ALL
THE IMPORTANT PEOPLE TRAVEL.
CUTE.
I CAN'T SEE A THING.
WHO PUT THE SAIL
IN FRONT OF EVERYTHING?
WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
BE ABLE TO MEET THE CHALLENGE
OF FIGHTING KEN
AND THEIR FRIEND AGUMON?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."