TK: We had to find
the last destiny stone
before Black Lord Greymon,
but troops travel better
on a full stomach,
so we went for Chinese food.
Would you believe the restaurant
belonged to Digitamamon?
And having the house special
were Arukenimon and Mummymon.
For some reason,
we couldn't digivolve,
but neither could they,
and they split.
Those two noodlebrains
were still hungry,
so they drank from
Digitamamon's secret soup pool.
And inside wasn't a wanton.
The last destiny stone.
Cody and I were finally
able to DNA digivolve
just in time too, cause
Shikuamon is our last chance
against Black War Greymon.
♪ Di Di Di ♪
♪ Digimon Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon
are the Champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon
are the Champions ♪
♪ Change into Digital Champions
to save the Digital World ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon
are the Champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon
are the Champions ♪
♪ Digivolve into Champions ♪
♪ Armor Digivolve ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon
are the Champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon
are the Champions ♪
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
♪ Digimon! ♪
‐ Ready?
‐ Yeah, let's go.
‐ Give it all you got.
‐ Yeah!
I'm Killomon!
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters ♪
Angemon!
BOTH: Here they
digivolve to:
VOICE: DNA digivolve!
Shakkuomon!
CODY: Shakkuomon
is the coolest thing out
since clumping glitter!
His enemies better
make travel plans,
because his kachina bombs
will send them flying.
We did it!
Finally!
Now we don't have to make
Paildramon and Silphymon
do all the hard work.
You said it.
Let him have it, Shakkuoman.
I'll prove my mettle.
GREYMON: You're
standing between me
and the last destiny stone.
Now get out of my way.
BOTH: Who's gonna make us?
Move or else.
We choose else.
Very well.
Terra Destroyer!
He's still too strong for us!
Ohh!
‐ ( gasps )
‐ Shakkuomon!
He swallowed up
Black War Greymon's terraforce!
Yeah!
Harmonious spirit.
Now, guys.
BOTH: Right.
You know the plan, Paildramon.
Right, no matter what,
protect the destiny stone.
Me first, static force!
You asked for it.
Hey, that's not fair!
‐ ( gasps )
‐ Now I'm angry.
Why do you persist this way?
You can't win.
Kachina Bomb.
Why do you keep trying to
protect the destiny stones?
BOTH: It's a little something
we call saving the world.
Desperado Blaster!
How can you be so certain
that what you
fight for is right?
Static Force!
I think we did it.
You're right.
I grow tired of this fight
I'm going to find my answer,
right here, right now.
It's over, we win!
I keep asking
questions of my enemies,
and yet I still
get no answers.
Why am I so different
from them?
Why was I created like this?
Well, if they won't answer me,
then why should I be
concerned about them anymore?
I've given every
opponent the chance
to convince me otherwise,
but now I am through talking.
Why should I care
if they are destroyed?
Or for that matter, their
whole precious digital world?
He seems so sad.
What he needs is a friend.
Destroying the destiny
stone means my own destruction
as well, but if
that's what it takes
to finally find my answer,
then so be it.
Don't take another
step or else.
I choose or else.
It's no use,
we can't stop him.
But if the destiny stone
is destroyed,
the whole digital
world will be lost.
I'm afraid it won't
only be the digiworld,
but our world
will be destroyed too.
Time for plan B.
By the way, does anybody know
what plan B is?
We could try moving the stone.
Good idea, let's do it while
the DNA digivolved digimon
are still able to hold
off Black War Greymon.
How can we lift that stone?
We'll never know
unless we try.
It's better
than doing nothing.
KARI: Davis is right.
Besides, no one has
any better ideas.
ARUKENIMON:
I have a better idea.
Say goodbye.
That's your cue to cry
and beg for mercy.
Ready to give up?
If you're ready to shut up.
Forget her, Davis,
she's not worth it.
( laughing )
You're trying to get me upset,
but it won't work.
Mummymon.
( cackling )
I'm going to put these kids
under wraps for the last time.
( evil laughter )
DIGITAMAMON:
Nightmare Syndrome!
I warned you not to drink out
of the Chinese soup spring.
You'll pay for that.
( grunts of pain )
Take care of
the destiny stone, kids!
Don't worry.
Thanks, Digitamamon,
thanks Tapermon.
Now's our chance, let's go.
How do we move that thing?
I got it.
Let's try using the old D3s.
( grunts of approval )
( beeping )
KARI: What are all those
lights doing?
CODY:
They're combining into one.
Just what I need,
another flashlight.
What are those kids
doing back there
with the destiny stone?
I just hope they
don't eat all the soup.
Mummymon, attack.
I'd rather not, thanks.
He came to life.
That's the same digimon
we saw when Black War Greymon
destroyed
the other destiny stone.
He's huge.
That guy's almost
as big as my appetite.
He better know how to fight,
cause Black War Greymon's
been looking for him.
Finally, my ultimate
opponent has appeared.
You.
You are the one with
the accursed soul of darkness.
Soul of darkness?
You can't mean me.
Tell me, why do you destroy
the destiny stones?
I did it to make you appear
so we can fight.
You are stronger than any
digimon I've ever seen before.
Do you have any idea who I am?
Only that you are
my ultimate opponent.
I am Azulonmon.
Azulonmon?
I am the guardian of the eastern
hemisphere of the digital world
and the keeper of the spheres
of light and hope.
Because you have destroyed
the destiny stones,
this world has
become unbalanced.
Do you understand
the consequences of
what you have done?
I don't care about
any of that nonsense.
Fight me, Azulonmon!
It is my destiny!
You fool.
You mean that's the reason
you caused all this suffering,
when it is your existence itself
that seals my power
and causes the unbalance
in this world?
My existence?
What do you mean?
I want the truth!
You can't handle the truth.
The control spires
here in the eastern region
were built to seal my power,
and you are made
from a hundred
of those spires.
You do the math.
What?
The control spires
seal his power?
And I was
the one that built them.
What does this mean?
All right,
so now you know, big deal.
It's Arukenimon.
Our plan was a simple one,
build as many control spires
as possible and destroy
the balance of the digital world
once and for all.
You got a problem,
so sue me.
And that's
the reason you chose me
to be the digimon emperor,
isn't it?
Because you knew I would build
those control spires for you.
You win the booby prize.
Unfortunately,
just as construction
was going along swimmingly,
you decided to join forces
with the other digidodos
and start destroying
all my precious control spires.
That's why I created you
to stop them,
but instead you wander
around the digital world
like a baby
looking for its bottle.
Didn't it ever occur to you
that digimon like yourself
have no souls of their own?
Put me down,
this is a brand‐new outfit.
Do you know how hard it is to
get wrinkles out of polyester?
Don't get mad at me because
fate has dealt you a bad hand.
Fate? Then why
am I standing here
within an inch
of destroying you?
Is that fate too?
AZULONMON:
Black War Greymon.
You ask more questions
than Cody does.
No one can answer them
but you.
You see, every life
has a purpose, a reason.
The circumstances surrounding
its birth don't matter.
You're saying that my life
has a meaning too?
Precisely. But it is up to you
to find out
what that meaning is.
Black War Greymon, I have
nothing more to tell you
unless you want to hear
a good joke Jenai told me
when I was in limbo.
Arukenimon!
I am grateful to have met you.
I now know that my existence
has meaning.
Even if that meaning is only
to be hated and loathed.
Where are you going?
Someplace where things
go to disappear.
He should try
my sock drawer.
Disappear?
‐ Mummymon, let's go.
‐ Where?
‐ To stop him, you fool.
‐ Oh, right.
Oh, don't go anywhere,
I'll be back to destroy
you in a minute.
Ditto that.
Destiny stones
can break my bones,
but you guys are real losers.
Oh, that's clever.
Did you write it yourself?
( laughing )
AZULONMON: And now for you,
digidestined.
I am one of the four megadigimon
who preserve the balance
of the digital world.
I protect the eastern region.
YOLEI: Hey,
that sounds like Kyoto.
Kyoto? How?
Remember
I told you about it?
I learned it
from Sora's dad.
The city is protected by
spirits in the east, west,
south, and north.
That's correct.
There are many similarities
between your world and ours.
After a long battle, we
guardians were sealed away
by each of the dark masters.
They didn't even
leave us something to read.
It was then that seven
of the eight digidestined
came to the digital world,
and once the seven had returned
to their own world,
the dark master dismantled it
and reshaped it
to fit their own needs.
KARI: Spiral mountain.
AZULONMON: The eight children
and their digimon
were able to defeat
the dark masters,
but we were still
trapped beneath the seal.
In order to break the seal,
we needed to take away
the power from
the digidestined crests.
Of course,
Joe complained about it,
but he complained
about everything.
Unfortunately, it meant that
digimon could no longer
digivolve to
their ultimate levels.
That is why our help
is needed now.
So that's the reason our
digimon could only digivolve
during certain times.
Hey, TK, this must be what
Izzy was talking about earlier.
Somehow he must have known
about Azulonmon.
Yes, Izzy is
quite intelligent.
In fact, without
that intelligence, he'd be,
well, he'd be Todd.
The dark power's control
spires kept the digimon
from being able to digivolve.
Those who wished for harmony
in the digital world
decided to use
an ancient form of digivolving.
You must mean
armor digivolving.
AZULONMON: Correct.
They chose several digimon
who still had
the ancient powers
and prepared them for
the arrival of the digidestined.
In other words,
they were drafted.
In order to combat
the powers of darkness,
they made three new digivices
and sent them
to the new digidestined.
Okay, now you're
talking about me, right?
Hello, the world doesn't
revolve around you.
He's talking
about all of us.
But something happened
that was not anticipated.
It seems you had
a device that was capable
of storing
several digieggs at once.
Sort of like
a digital egg carton.
I believe you called
it a D‐terminal.
So when the digieggs
of sincerity, friendship,
and reliability were needed,
they were given to you.
Also the crest
of kindness was hidden
by the powers of darkness,
so it was necessary
to rebuild it
into the digiegg of miracles.
It wasn't easy, so we hired
a general contractor.
( growling )
KARI: He sounds so sad.
My friend,
I feel your agony.
I hope that one day
you will find the answer
to your question.
Well, at least now
you can regain your power,
right, Azulonmon?
Uh, not right away.
The digital world
is too unbalanced.
First, I must plant
my seeds of light
where the destiny stones
once stood
and hope for the best.
I've never had much
of a green thumb.
What kind of seeds of light?
The seeds that will sprout
and take on the same purpose
as the destiny stones.
That's a relief.
And then the balance
of the digital world
will be restored
little by little.
How about that, guys,
we really did it.
Looks that way.
Now that's what I call‐‐ huh?
What's wrong with you, Ken?
‐ Why so quiet?
‐ Nothing.
Come on, if you've
got something to say,
then just say it already.
I was just thinking that
we might just have to find
and destroy every single
thing that has to do
with the powers of darkness.
Otherwise they will continue
to grow bigger and bigger
and before you know it, we'll
have a bunch more creatures
like Black War Greymon
roaming around.
Oh, no, Ken.
You can't be serious, Ken.
KARI: ( thinking )
Ken understands
the powers of darkness
more than any of us.
After all, he's the one
that first created Chimeramon.
I don't think
that'll be necessary.
What?
I agree that the powers of
darkness are a terrible thing.
And I think I speak
for all of us by saying
it would be easier
if they were destroyed.
But I just don't think
that it's possible.
But why not?
Because where there's light,
you'll always find
darkness as well.
TK's right, and the stronger
the light is,
then the deeper the darkness.
Exactly. So we have to
remember that no matter how
the powers of
darkness surround you,
the most important thing is
not to lose the light inside.
But I don't understand.
What is the light inside?
The light inside is hope.
What?
When all around you
is darkness,
you must keep the light on
inside your heart,
no matter how high
your electric bill gets.
It's the same
as the crest of hope.
KARI:
The light in your heart?
After the dark
masters were defeated,
those bearing the crests
of light and hope
were the ones
that broke my seal.
Hey, TK,
those were our crests.
When the dark digivice was
brought into the digital world,
the harmonious ones were only
able to find three digimon
who had the ancient power
of armor digivolving.
However, the digimon
belonging to the digidestined
with the crest of light
and hope also were capable
of the same power.
So their digivices
took on new form,
allowing them
to armor digivolve as well.
TK: Pegasusmon
and Nepherdimon!
These two crests,
light and hope,
are different
from the others.
The crest of courage,
the crest of love,
and the crest of knowledge
come from the power
inside the digidestined's
hearts.
But the crest of light
gives life to this world.
And the crest of hope
continues to shine
no matter how darkness
tries to hide it.
Once all the digidestined
joined their hearts together,
the power was born, and
the light shone even brighter.
Giving the digimon
the ability to digivolve.
It is because of you,
digidestined,
that the digital world
still exists.
But even though
Black War Greymon is gone
and my power will
soon be restored, beware,
for the threat is not over.
‐ ( gasps )
‐ What are you saying?
The evil that tried to seal
me away has not disappeared.
Are you talking about
Arukenimon and Mummymon?
No. They are merely pawns.
There is an even
greater hatred in existence.
You mean someone else
is controlling Arukenimon?
Then that's who was
controlling me too.
Your job is not finished.
You must not stop
until the digital world
is safe once and for all.
We'll keep one eye
on the digiworld
and one eye on our world.
And we'll keep the other eye
on each other.
AZULONMON:
Hm. You must be Davis.
Well, despite him, I wish you
all good luck in your quest.
ALL: Goodbye! Goodbye!
Thanks to you, I am able
to return to my restaurant.
How about some treats?
DIGITAMAMON:
I know they're not much,
but take them, please.
ALL: All right, free food!
What's the matter
with you, Davis?
Didn't you see me,
I was reaching for that one!
They're all the same,
aren't they?!
TK: Here, Ken.
They're really good.
Aren't you going to try one?
Okay, I'll try one.
( voracious devouring )
Is it good?
( approving grunts )
I agree.
I said that one's mine!
DAVIS:
Those Chinese buns were great.
YOLEI:
You had one more than me.
Well, I didn't know
you were counting.
Let me tell you something,
when it comes to food,
I always count.
What are you looking at?
Well, I'm not exactly sure,
but I think I just saw
a control spire.
You should try wearing
those goggles once in a while.
Control spire? Yeah, right.
DAVIS: ( thinking )
I don't care what Yolei says.
I know what I saw.
NARRATOR:
What is this new evil
that Azulonmon spoke of?
Are the digidestined
strong enough to face it?
Find out on the next
Digimon: Digital Monsters!
( Saban jingle )
( ending theme playing )