T.K.: IMPERIALDRAMON
DROPPED US OFF AROUND THE PLANET
SO WE COULD
CAPTURE THE DIGIMON
AND SEND THEM
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
DAVIS, KEN, AND MATT
WENT TO THE U.S.
WHERE THEY GOT TO MEET
MICHAEL'S FATHER,
A REAL-LIFE MOVIE STAR.
MIMI JOINED THEM
IN NEW YORK.
IN CENTRAL PARK,
THEY RAN INTO BENJAMIN,
WHO LOOKS JUST LIKE GENNAI
BUT MAKES A BETTER HOT DOG.
MEANWHILE, IN HONG KONG,
KARI, IZZY, AND JACKIE,
ANOTHER GENNAI LOOK-ALIKE,
MET UP WITH THE POI BROTHERS
TO BATTLE THE DIGIMON THERE.
IZZY AND THE OTHERS
WENT TO INDIA,
WHERE THE CHINESE ARMY WAS
ABOUT TO ATTACK THE DIGIMON,
BUT KARI CAME UP WITH A PLAN
TO STOP THEM.
LOOK, WE ALL LIKE TO TRAVEL,
BUT THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Cody: IT SURE
WOULD BE NICE
TO SPEND A LITTLE TIME
HERE ON THE BEACH,
BUT FIRST THINGS FIRST.
DIGMON, YOU READY?
YOU BET.
JUST SAY THE WORD, CODY.
Joe: IKKAKUMON, TAKE CARE
OF THAT CONTROL SPIRE.
RIGHT. HARPOON TORPEDO!
EASY THERE, PARTNER.
SAVE SOME FOR ME.
ROCK CRACKING!
IT'S CHRISTMASTIME
AND IT'S HOT.
I'M SWEATING MORE NOW
THAN THE LAST TIME
I GOT MY TEETH CLEANED
AT THE DENTIST.
DON'T FORGET
WE'RE IN AUSTRALIA, JOE.
IT'S THEIR SUMMER
RIGHT NOW.
ON CHRISTMAS, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO WEAR SWEATERS,
NOT SUNSCREEN.
IT'S LIKE THEY DON'T HAVE
A CARE IN THE WORLD.
EVERYONE ELSE
IS GOING NUTS,
AND ALL THEY WANT TO DO
IS HAVE FUN.
THAT'S HOW THINGS ARE
IN AUSTRALIA --
LAID-BACK AND EASYGOING.
IT'S SORT OF HOW
I USED TO BE
BEFORE I DECIDED
TO GO INTO MEDICINE.
Digmon: YOU'D THINK
THEY WOULD BE A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT ALL THESE
CONTROL SPIRES POPPING UP.
THEY PROBABLY THINK
THEY'RE SOME KIND
OF LIFEGUARD TOWER
FOR SHARK WATCHING.
LET'S KNOCK THEM DOWN.
YEAH, CODY AND I
WILL DO THE HEAVE,
YOU GUYS DO THE HO.
AND HEAVE!
GO!
I DIDN'T SAY "GO,"
I SAID "HO."
Ikkakumon: JOE?
NO -- HO, HO, HO!
DID SOMEONE SAY
"HO HO HO"?
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO DELIVER
SOME TOYS ON MY JET SKI
WHEN I SAW
YOU COULD USE A HAND.
Both: SANTA CLAUS
ON A JET SKI?
YOU SHOULD SEE ME
ON A SURFBOARD. NOW PULL!
Both: WE DID IT!
YAY!
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
NO TIME
FOR SIPPING EGGNOG NOW.
ALL THE DIGIDESTINED
HERE IN AUSTRALIA
ARE LEADING THE DIGIMON
TO THE GREAT BARRIER REEF,
WHERE THE LAST CONTROL SPIRE
IS STILL STANDING. AH.
Both: WHOA, IT'S GENNAI!
ACTUALLY, THE NAME'S HOGAN.
I'M GENNAI'S FRIEND.
Boy: HELP!
SOMEBODY HELP ME,
PLEASE!
Cody: THERE'S A BOY
ON THAT SAILBOARD.
Armadillomon: LOOKS LIKE
HE'S BEING CHASED BY A SHARK.
Joe: LOOK, HE'S GOT
A DIGIMON WITH HIM.
YOU'RE RIGHT, WHICH MEANS
THAT BOY IS A DIGIDESTINED,
JUST LIKE YOU TWO.
AAH!
THAT'S NOT A SHARK
CHASING HIM!
I HOPE HE'S REALLY GOOD
WITH THAT SAILBOARD,
'CAUSE HE'S GOT
THREE DIGIMON ON HIS TAIL!
Ikkakumon: I KNOW THOSE GUYS.
THAT'S GESOMON, SHELLMON,
AND EBIDRAMON.
GESOMON?
SHELLMON?
EBIDRAMON?
SOUNDS LIKE THE SPECIAL
AT THE REVOLVING SUSHI BAR.
YEAH -- REVOLVING.
YOU GOT AN IDEA?
IKKAKUMON?
I GOTCHA, JOE.
DIGIMON, DON'T JUST SURF.
PUT A LITTLE SPIN
ON IT!
AAH!
THAT WAS A BEAUT!
[ ALL GROWL ]
DON'T EVEN BOTHER
DRYING OFF.
YEAH, YOU WON'T BE
STAYING HERE THAT LONG.
THANKS A LOT
FOR THE TIP, MATE.
IT THREW THEM
FOR A LOOP.
NAME'S DERRICK.
YOU BLOKES DIGIDESTINED?
YEAH, WE'RE THE "A" TEAM.
AND WHO'S THIS?
I'M CRABMON.
I'LL USE MY SCISSORS ATTACK
ON ANYONE
WHO GETS IN MY WAY.
IF YOU NEED HELP,
CALL ME IN A PINCH.
SORRY, GUYS. THERE'LL BE
TIME FOR INTRODUCTIONS LATER.
HEY, IKKAKUMON,
ARE YOU GETTING HUNGRY?
ABSOLUTELY. I'M THINKING
OF HAVING A LARGE PIZZA
WITH GESOMON SAUSAGE,
SHELLMON PEPPERONI,
AND EXTRA EBIDRAMON CHEESE.
SAUSAGE?
PEPPERONI?
AND CHEESE PIZZA?
Ikkakumon: DON'T FORGET
THE HOT SAUCE.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
Cody: ARMADILLOMON, I BET
YOU COULD USE A BITE.
ACTUALLY, I'M IN THE MOOD
FOR A TRIPLE-DIP
DIGIMON RICE PILAF.
TRIPLE-DIP...
DIGIMON...
RICE...
PILAF?
[ ALL SCREAM ]
CRABMON, IT'S WORKING.
WHY DON'T YOU SHOW THESE GUYS
HOW WE TAKE CARE
OF THINGS DOWN UNDER?
I KIND OF LIKE
THE RICE PART,
BUT LET'S SPICE IT UP --
JAMBALAYA.
All: PLEASE, NO!
ANYTHING BUT THAT!
Ikkakumon: AND WHEN
WE'RE DONE,
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE YOU
INTO OUR FAVORITE DESSERT.
BROWNIE!
ICE CREAM!
PIE!
THEY'RE HEADED
FOR THE GREAT BARRIER REEF.
HANG ON TIGHT,
EVERYBODY.
Cody: JOE, YOU'RE LOOKING
A LITTLE GREEN.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FEELING
A BIT SEASICK.
FORTUNATELY, IT ONLY HAPPENS
WHENEVER I'M AROUND WATER.
Hogan: THERE IT IS --
THE GREAT BARRIER REEF.
AND LOOK OVER THERE.
THE LAST CONTROL SPIRE.
WE'LL WORRY ABOUT
THOSE THREE LATER.
FIRST WE HAVE TO DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE.
All: YEAH!
Joe: IKKAKUMON,
LET THEM GO.
All: WHEW,
THAT WAS TOO CLOSE.
WITH ALL THIS TALK ABOUT
FOOD, I'M GETTING HUNGRY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE ALL GO OUT FOR --
AAH!
FIRST YOU HAVE TO GET
PAST ME -- SCORPIOMON.
AAH!
Crabmon: I'LL HANDLE
THIS LOWLIFE,
PENNY-PINCHING ARACHNID.
YAAH!
OOF!
NO ONE CALLS ME
ARACHNID!
HE'S TOO STRONG FOR US.
IKKAKUMON,
YOU'VE GOT TO DIGIVOLVE.
IKKAKUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ZUDOMON!
WHOA!
TAIL BLADE!
THEY'RE DESTROYING
ALL THE CORAL IN THE REEF.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
IF WE LET THEM
KEEP FIGHTING LIKE THIS,
THE ENTIRE BARRIER REEF
WILL BE WIPED OUT.
ZUDOMON, UNDERWATER.
YEAH, WHEN IT COMES TO WATER,
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
SUBMARIMON!
CRABMON, IT'S YOUR TURN.
CRABMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
COELAMON!
THAT'S COELAMON.
IF YOU THOUGHT
CRABMON WAS CRABBY,
WAIT TILL YOU SEE THIS GUY'S
FOSSIL BITE ATTACK.
HE'LL WIPE OUT HIS ENEMIES
HOOK, LINE, AND SINKER.
SUBMARIMON,
WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO LEAD SCORPIOMON
AWAY FROM THE CORAL REEF.
YOU GOT IT!
OXYGEN TORPEDO!
[ GRUNTS ]
I KNOW HOW TO GET HIM
TO FOLLOW ME.
ARACHNID, ARACHNID,
ARACHNID!
VULCAN'S HAMMER!
OXYGEN TORPEDO!
WOW, HE'S OUT COLD.
MAYBE OUR ATTACK
WAS TOO STRONG.
HE'LL BE OKAY.
I THINK HE JUST FAINTED.
[ ALL CHEER ]
NOW WE CAN FINALLY
DESTROY THE CONTROL SPIRE.
Zudomon: ALL RIGHT,
I'M GOING TO TAKE A SHOT
AT THE BASE OF IT.
SUBMARIMON, I WANT YOU
TO ATTACK FROM THE SIDE.
THEN WE CAN --
FORGET THAT.
FOSSIL BITE!
Zudomon: OR THAT
WILL WORK, TOO.
[ GROANING AND CRYING ]
[ CHEERING ]
THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED
HAVE LED THE DIGIMON
RIGHT TO US.
WE CAN
SEND THEM ALL HOME
AND BE BACK IN TIME
FOR THE BARBECUE.
GOOD ON YA!
DO YOU THINK THEY'LL HAVE
SOMETHING MILD?
MY STOMACH'S STILL QUEASY.
OKAY, DIGIPORT OPEN.
Joe: HEY, DERRICK,
I'VE GOT ANOTHER QUESTION.
WHY DO THEY CALL IT
"DOWN UNDER"?
IT'S NOT REALLY
UNDER ANYTHING.
T.K.: WOW, CHECK OUT
THE EIFFEL TOWER!
THAT'S GOT TO BE
THE WORLD'S TALLEST
CHRISTMAS TREE.
Tai: YEAH, AND I'D LOVE
TO STAND AROUND
AND LOOK AT THE DECORATIONS
ON THE ARC DE TRIOMPHE,
BUT I'VE GOT
TWO PROBLEMS.
ONE, WE'VE GOT TO FIND
THE CONTROL SPIRES,
AND TWO,
I'M FREEZING OUT HERE.
T.K., YOU TOLD ME
YOUR GRANDFATHER MICHEL
LIVES HERE IN PARIS
AND WOULD BE WILLING
TO LEND US A HAND.
SO WHERE IS HE?
LISTEN, TAI,
IF MY GRANDFATHER SAYS
HE'S GOING TO DO SOMETHING,
WELL, 8 TIMES OUT OF 10,
HE'S GOING TO DO IT.
WHAT IF THIS IS ONE
OF THE OTHER TWO TIMES?
WE DON'T KNOW
OUR WAY AROUND PARIS,
AND NEITHER ONE OF US
SPEAKS ANY FRENCH.
I TOLD HIM THIS TIME
IT WAS AN EMERGENCY,
SO DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL BE HERE.
AAH!
Agumon: UH-OH. HERE COMES
ONE OF THOSE BIKER GUYS,
AND HE LOOKS
PRETTY MEAN, TOO.
T.K.!
GRANDPA, HEY!
HA HA HA HA HA!
ARE YOU READY TO SING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW YOU HAVE TO
SING "FRèRE JACQUES"
EVERY TIME YOU SEE ME.
GRANDPA, THE WORLD'S
IN A LOT OF DANGER.
HE'S RIGHT. THE FUTURE
OF EARTH DEPENDS ON US.
THERE'S NO TIME
FOR SINGING.
DANGER OR NO DANGER,
THERE'S ALWAYS TIME
FOR SINGING.
HEY, GRANDPA, WHY DIDN'T
YOU BRING GRANDMA ALONG?
SHE WAS FINISHING UP
SOME PLUMBING WORK
IN THE KITCHEN.
ANYWAY, WHENEVER WE GO
FOR A RIDE ON THIS THING,
SHE ALWAYS
INSISTS ON DRIVING.
I UNDERSTAND.
BESIDES, I HAVE
A STRANGE FEELING
THINGS ARE GOING TO GET
A LITTLE ROUGH HERE TONIGHT.
THIS CALLS FOR SOMEONE
TOUGH AND DOMINATING.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
SHE'S RIGHT FOR THE JOB.
I DON'T REALLY CARE
WHO IT IS,
AS LONG AS WE FIND
AND DESTROY THE CONTROL SPIRES.
THIS WASN'T HOW I WAS PLANNING
TO SPEND MY CHRISTMAS EVE.
I KNOW, GRANDPA.
IF ALL GOES WELL,
WHEN WE WAKE UP TOMORROW,
IT'LL BE JUST AS IF NOTHING
EVER HAPPENED --
A NICE PEACEFUL
CHRISTMAS MORNING.
NOT AT MY HOUSE.
GRANDMA'S PUTTING UP
A NEW ROOF TOMORROW.
HANG ON TIGHT.
SHE ADJUSTED THE BRAKES
LAST WEEK.
[ ALL GASP ]
WHY DID YOU STOP,
GRANDPA?
MM, SOMETHING
IS NOT RIGHT HERE.
Tai: WHAT IS IT?
IT'S THE GATE
TO VERSAILLES PALACE.
SHE IS WIDE OPEN.
AND LOOK INSIDE --
THERE ARE NO GUARDS,
AND SHE'S ALL LIT UP.
QU'EST QUE CE PAS?
Agumon: SO WHAT?
IT'S PROBABLY BEING USED
FOR ONE OF THOSE
SECRET CELEBRITY WEDDINGS.
NO! THIS IS NOT ONE
OF THOSE RENTAL HALLS
THAT SERVES
RUBBER CHICKEN.
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T
MEAN ANYTHING BY IT.
IT WAS
JUST A JOKE, SIR.
I'M NOT LAUGHING.
GRANDPA, COME ON.
LET'S GET GOING.
IT'S MY RESPONSIBILITY
AS A FRENCHMAN
TO INVESTIGATE THE MATTER,
AND IF NEED BE, TO ACT ON IT.
SO IT'S OPEN.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
TO THE FRENCH
IS A GOOD BAKERY,
AND THE SECOND
IS VERSAILLES PALACE.
VIVE LA FRANCE!
WAIT! BUT WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO TELL GRANDMA?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
IF SHE SAW THIS GATE
WAS LEFT UNATTENDED,
SHE WOULD HAVE
SOMEONE'S HEAD ON A PLATTER.
WHENEVER THE GATE
NEEDS REPAIRS,
WHO DO YOU THINK
THEY CALL? LET'S GO.
WAIT UP!
T.K.!
"LET'S CALL MY GRANDPA.
HE CAN HELP US.
HE'S AN EASYGOING GUY."
T.K.: ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
Michel: PREPARE
FOR THE BATTLE OF VERSAILLES!
OKAY, THE SECOND ONE.
[ EATING AND LAUGHING ]
SHH.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HUH?
OH!
GOOD JUICE.
WHO ARE THOSE GUYS?
Agumon: THAT'S MAMEMON.
DON'T LET HIS SIZE FOOL YOU.
WHAT HE LACKS IN HEIGHT,
HE MAKES UP FOR
WITH HIS SMIRK BOMB ATTACK.
Both: BUT WAIT.
THAT'S NOT ALL.
Patamon: THAT'S BIGMAMEMON.
DON'T LET HIS SIZE
FOOL YOU, EITHER.
HE LOOKS SLOW,
BUT WATCH OUT
FOR HIS BIG SMIRK BOMB ATTACK.
Both: OKAY, WELL,
THEN WHO'S THE THIRD ONE?
Agumon: HE'S METAL MAMEMON.
BEING A CYBORG TYPE DIGIMON,
HE'S THE STRONGEST OF ALL.
HIS METAL SMIRK BOMBS
ARE IRONCLAD.
Tai: THESE ARE
SOME OF THE DIGIMON
WHO ARE PUTTING
THE WORLD IN DANGER?
OH, THEY'VE GOT
A LOT OF NERVE.
IT'S ONE THING
TO ATTACK THE WORLD,
BUT TO INVADE
VERSAILLES PALACE!
GRANDPA,
YOU'VE GOT TO CALM DOWN.
Agumon: HEY, LOOK!
I THINK THERE'S
SOMEONE ELSE IN THERE.
[ GASPS ]
T.K. and Tai:
ALL RIGHT!
LOOK THERE!
Both: ALL RIGHT!
[ GASPS ]
SHE HAS A DIGIMON.
THAT CAN MEAN
ONLY ONE THING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE'S A DIGIDESTINED.
VERY WELL.
STAND ASIDE.
YOU THERE --
BIGMAMEMON.
HUH?
BONJOUR. ON BEHALF
OF THE PEOPLE
OF THE FRENCH REPUBLIC,
I CHARGE YOU WITH TRESPASSING,
AND I'M HEREBY PLACING YOU
UNDER CITIZEN'S ARREST,
N'EST-CE PAS?
MADEMOISELLE, I WOULD
GREATLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU WOULD ALLOW ME
THE HONOR OF RESCUING YOU.
AH!
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN US
FOR DESSERT?
HERE!
[ LAUGHING ]
HEY, THAT'S NOT --
AGUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
PATAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
Bigmamemon:
LET'S STEP OUTSIDE.
HEY, USE THE DOOR!
HAND OF FATE!
NOVA BLAST!
METAL SMIRK BOMB!
FIREWORKS AT CHRISTMAS.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
OH, MADEMOISELLE,
I ALMOST FORGOT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YES, I AM OKAY.
I WANT TO THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
FORGIVE ME.
MY NAME IS CATHERINE.
I AM ONE OF THE DIGIDESTINED
HERE IN FRANCE.
I AM JUST GRATEFUL
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
I AM FINE, REALLY.
UH, CATHERINE,
HOW DID THEY CAPTURE YOU?
WELL, FLORAMON AND I
WERE TRYING TO DESTROY
A CONTROL SPIRE
NEAR THE SEINE RIVER.
NO ONE WAS AROUND.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE EASY.
RAIN OF POLLEN!
[ Laughs ]
BING, BANG, BOOM!
[ BOTH GASP ]
THE NEXT THING I KNEW,
WE WERE PRISONERS
HERE IN VERSAILLES PALACE.
YOU ARE LUCKY
TO BE ALIVE.
SO THE MAMEMON BROTHERS
AREN'T THE ONLY DIGIMON
IN FRANCE.
PARLEZ-VOUS GIROMON?
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU CAN'T GET MUCH NASTIER
THAN ME, THAT'S FOR SURE.
MY SPINNING MINE ATTACK
WILL SINK YOUR SHIP.
METAL SMIRK BOMB!
HOW DOES THIS FEEL?
SPINNING MINE!
BIG SMIRK BOMB!
THEY'RE ULTIMATES.
WE CAN'T COMPETE
WITH THEM LIKE THIS.
GREYMON, YOU'VE GOT
TO DIGIVOLVE.
YOU BETTER DIGIVOLVE TOO,
ANGEMON.
AND YOU, FLORAMON!
ANGEMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
MAGNAANGEMON!
GREYMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
METAL GREYMON!
GRRAAH!
FLORAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
KIWIMON!
BIG SMIRK BOMB!
PUMMEL PECK!
Giromon: LET'S
GET OUT OF HERE!
Tai: ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE ON THE RUN.
LET'S GET THEM DOWN
TO THE CONTROL SPIRE
BY THE SEINE.
NO PROBLEM.
CATHERINE, IF YOU GET SCARED,
GRAB ONTO ME.
T.K.: ACTUALLY, I'M CLOSER,
SO GRAB ME.
GIGA BLASTER!
[ ALL CHEER ]
Tai: WELL, GUYS, I'D SAY
WE JUST SAVED THE WORLD.
THE OTHER DIGIDESTINED
ARE PROBABLY RETURNING HOME.
GRANDMA'S PROBABLY
REMODELED THE HOUSE.
All: GOODBYE!
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
BYE! AU REVOIR!
GENTLEMEN, LET ME SHOW YOU
THE PROPER WAY.
GOODBYE.
AH!
Girl: [ COUGHING ]
Boy: BOY, YOUR COUGH
SOUNDS REALLY BAD.
YEAH, YOU BETTER
GO HOME.
I AM.
BYE. FEEL BETTER.
HUH?
THERE'S SOMETHING SCARY
ABOUT THAT LADY,
BUT SOMEHOW IT SEEMS
LIKE SHE UNDERSTANDS ME.
I HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHO SHE IS.
THE DIGIDESTINED
MAY HAVE SAVED THE EARTH,
BUT WHAT'S THE NEW TROUBLE
BREWING IN JAPAN?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."