I DON'T KNOW HOW TO EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME.
I DREAMED ABOUT MY BROTHER SAM
AND THE FIRST TIME
WE SAW A DIGIVICE.
SAM THOUGHT IT WAS HIS
AND WOULDN'T LET ME TOUCH IT,
BUT I WAS THE ONE DESTINED
TO BECOME THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
LUCKY ME. I WISH I'D
NEVER READ THAT E-MAIL.
WHEN I WOKE UP,
I WAS CONFUSED,
BUT I REMEMBERED MY PROMISE
TO WORMMON TO ALWAYS BE KIND.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I WENT BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT IT'S A GOOD THING I DID.
HE CAME BACK AS LEAFMON!
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
DELICIOUS, DEAR.
SO TELL US,
HOW WAS SOCCER?
UM, I DID OKAY, MOM.
SOME MORE RICE?
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
THAT YOU EAT WELL,
FOR YOUR BRAIN AND BODY.
YOU MAY NOT SEE IT,
BUT YOU'RE GROWING
ALL THE TIME, SON.
I'LL HAVE ANOTHER
HALF A BOWL, PLEASE.
SURE.
OH, KEN,
TOMORROW SOCCER PRACTICE
HAS BEEN POSTPONED.
THIS BEEF STEW IS DELICIOUS.
CAN I HAVE SOME MORE?
IT'S CHICKEN PARMESAN.
OH. NEVER MIND.
WHEW.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT IS IT, KEN?
OH, NOTHING, REALLY.
I JUST ATE TOO MUCH
AT DINNER.
THAT DOESN'T
SOUND LIKE YOU.
NORMALLY
I JUST EAT ONE BOWL,
BUT MY FOLKS
SEEMED CONCERNED,
SO I ATE A LITTLE MORE
THAN I USUALLY DO.
YOU ATE MORE
FOR YOUR PARENTS?
WHO WOULD HAVE
EVER THOUGHT THAT?
BOY, WERE THEY HAPPY!
I MIGHT HAVE TO START
EATING LIKE THIS EVERY DAY!
UH-OH. IN THAT CASE,
THERE'S ONLY
ONE THING TO DO.
JUMPING JACKS!
WHOO-HOO! COME ON, KEN!
FEEL THE BURN!
CRUNCH THOSE ABS!
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE BUFF ENOUGH.
LET'S GET SOME SLEEP.
[ GASPS ]
HMM?
WHAT IS IT, KEN?
HEY, WHO ARE YOU?
EMPEROR, ARE YOU
HAVING TROUBLE SLEEPING?
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE THROUGH!
WHAT?
WHO -- WHO ARE YOU?
YOU ARE JUST SO USELESS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU KNOW ABOUT ME?
YOU HAD SO MUCH POTENTIAL.
HUH?
IS SHE GONE?
I HOPE SO.
YOLEI, I'M SO TIRED
OF LIFTING THIS PAINTBRUSH
THAT MY WHOLE BODY
IS SHAKING.
OH. NEVER MIND.
AAH. WE'RE QUITE
A DRILL TEAM, DIGMON.
HEY, LOOKING GOOD, GUYS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
Davis: WELL, THAT WAS
A GOOD DAY'S WORK.
Yolei: YEAH.
GOOD WORK, EVERYONE.
Kari: WE PAINTED
EVERYTHING IN SIGHT.
AND DAVIS
ALMOST STRAINED HIS VOICE
FROM SHOUTING ORDERS.
EVEN WITH FRESH PAINT
AND SOME NEW ROOFS,
PRIMARY VILLAGE
STILL SEEMS KIND OF SAD.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE A CUTE CARPENTER
WILL COME BY.
Cody: THE ONLY PLACE
HE'S GOING IS TO WORK.
I VOLUNTEER
TO BE HIS HELPER!
T.K.: THAT JERK LEFT
THE DIGITAL WORLD
IN A BIG MESS,
DIDN'T HE?
Davis: IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I'M DOING THE BEST I CAN.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT KEN,
NOT YOU, DAVIS.
OH. NEVER MIND.
NO HARM, NO FOUL.
YOU'VE GOT TO WONDER,
WHAT IS HE UP TO NOW?
IS HE JUST PLAYING WITH US
SO WE THINK HE'S NICE?
IF HE REALLY IS NICE,
HE'D BE HERE CLEANING UP.
Armadillomon:
THAT'S FOR SURE!
Yolei: BUT KEN'S
NOT COMING BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
RIGHT?
Hawkmon: ONE WOULDN'T
THINK SO.
I DON'T THINK THE DIGIMON
COULD FORGIVE HIM.
HMM. THAT'S FOR SURE.
YOU SOUND MAD.
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I CAN'T FORGIVE HIM, EITHER.
NOT EVER.
Davis: WELL, LET'S GET BACK
TO THE REAL WORLD.
I'M STARVING!
Kari: DAVIS, PARTY OF ONE,
LET'S GET GOING.
I GOT A KENDO LESSON
TO GET TO. SEE YOU LATER.
YEAH. SEE YOU.
GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO
PIG OUT WITHOUT YOU.
HAVE FUN AT YOUR LESSON.
AND NOW WHAT TIME IS IT?
All: IT'S TIME TO MUNCH!
HEY, WHAT IS THIS? HUH?
HMM.
[ GROANS ]
HYAH!
GRR. HA HA HA HA.
HA HA HA HA.
AH, EXCELLENT, CODY.
THIS IS ALL FOR TODAY.
[ PANTING ]
YES, SIR.
THANK YOU, SENSEI.
[ GROANS ]
GRANDPA?
LOOK, CHECK THESE OUT.
THEY'RE LIQUID YOGURT PACKS.
OH...
I ALWAYS EAT YOGURT
WITH A SPOON, RIGHT?
WRONG.
LAST WEEK, I SAID,
"WHAT THE HECK?"
AND TRIED IT THIS WAY.
I LEARNED I REALLY PREFERRED
DRINKING MY YOGURT
INSTEAD OF EATING IT
WITH A SPOON.
OH...
A LIGHT WENT ON,
AND I REALIZED
WE NEVER STOP LEARNING
IF WE JUST KEEP TRYING.
IT'S AN INTERESTING LESSON.
AHH...MM.
[ GULPING ]
[ SNORING LOUDLY ]
OOH! AAH!
JUST A LITTLE LOWER,
POROMON.
YEAH! THAT'S GREAT!
FINALLY, I DID IT!
WAIT TILL DAVIS SEES THIS.
HE'LL FLIP!
AH-AH...
AH-CHOO!
"AND CATPUNZEL WOULD LET DOWN
HER PERSIAN HAIR
SO HE COULD CLIMB UP."
MM-HMM.
AHH!
MMM...
[ Thinking ] GRANDPA'S RIGHT.
BEING FLEXIBLE IS IMPORTANT.
Davis: SHOOTS,
HE SCORES!
[ CRASH ]
OH, NO.
Man: AND IF THIS HAPPENS
AGAIN, YOUNG MAN,
YOU WILL BE TALKING
TO THE PRINCIPAL.
YES, SIR,
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
Patamon: WHAT TOOK YOU
SO LONG?
SOME TEACHERS ARE NITPICKERS
ABOUT SUCH LITTLE THINGS!
Yolei: WHAT WAS IT
THIS TIME?
I WAS ACCIDENTALLY
PLAYING SOCCER INDOORS,
AND SOMEHOW
A WINDOW BROKE.
BOY, MR. REYNOLDS
SURE IS A GROUCH.
NOT AGAIN.
IT'S THE FOURTH TIME, BUT, HEY,
WHO'S COUNTING, RIGHT?
HUH? I THOUGHT
IT WAS AT LEAST SIX!
[ ALL LAUGH ]
Yolei: ALL RIGHT.
READY?
BACK TO PRIMARY VILLAGE
WE GO!
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH,
O-O-OH ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH,
O-O-O-OH ♪
All: AI, AI, AI, AI!
Davis: WE HAVE NEW FRIENDS.
Voices:
LET'S PLAY! LET'S PLAY!
Cody: WELL, THEY SURE
WEREN'T HERE YESTERDAY.
Armadillomon: MAYBE
IT'S 'CAUSE, YESTERDAY,
WE REBUILT
THE NURSERY SCHOOL.
NO WAY!
THAT WAS A NURSERY SCHOOL?
Hawkmon: SO LOGIC DICTATES
THEY WERE ALL STUDENTS THERE.
Yolei: SO IF WE RESTORE THINGS
TO THE WAY THEY WERE,
THEN ALL OF THE DIGIMON
WILL RETURN AS WELL, RIGHT?
Voices: YAY!
RIGHT.
SO LET'S KEEP WORKING.
YOU'RE A MAJOR PAIN.
AW...THEY'RE CUTE!
OH...
THEY'RE SO SWEET.
Veemon: THAT'S NOT WHAT
YOU SAID A SECOND AGO.
VEEMON, LET'S GIVE THIS
OUR BEST SHOT TODAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
VEEMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
VEE...
UH-OH!
AND WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT?
YOU GOT TO TRY HARDER!
DIGIVOLVE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
VEEMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
VEEMON.
I'M STILL VEEMON.
I GUESS MY BIORHYTHM'S
OFF TODAY.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
YOU ATE A TON, AND YOU
DIGIVOLVED FINE YESTERDAY.
WHY CAN'T I DIGIVOLVE?
[ Sobs ] TELL ME WHY!
I'M DONE.
MAYBE YOU'RE JUST TIRED.
MAYBE IT'S SOME KIND
OF DIGI-JET LAG.
Hawkmon: IS THERE ANY CHANCE
YOU ATE SOME BAD CHOCOLATE?
MAYBE CHICKEN SOUP
MIGHT HELP, HUH?
BUT HIS STOMACH'S FULL.
HE HAD FOUR TV DINNERS.
MAYBE HE OVERATE.
HE HASN'T FOUGHT IN SO LONG
THAT HE'S RUSTY.
IT'S LIKE HE'S TOTALLY
OUT OF SHAPE
WHEN IT COMES
TO DIGIVOLVING.
THAT MUST BE IT.
YOU JUST NEED TO RELAX,
AND DO SOMETHING TO TAKE
YOUR MIND OFF OF THIS.
BOTH OF YOU NEED A BREAK
FROM ALL THIS HARD WORK.
THEY'RE GOING BACK TO WORK
WHILE THE FOUR OF US REST.
I COULD USE
A LITTLE NAP MYSELF.
WE'RE GOING TO GO
OUTSIDE OF TOWN.
WE HAVE TO CHECK
SOMETHING OUT.
WE'LL BE BACK
IN AN HOUR.
HEY, I KNOW SOMETHING WE CAN DO
THAT'S REALLY RELAXING.
HA!
YOLEI!
Gatomon: NO GO
FOR GATO.
ALL RIGHT, PATAMON,
YOU TRY IT.
GIVE IT YOUR ALL!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
PATAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
[ Sadly ] PATAMON.
I NEED A BREAK.
WE'RE NOT AMATEURS LIKE
VEEMON. WHAT'S GOING ON?
Kari: IT'S PRETTY STRANGE.
BOY.
HMM.
I THOUGHT
THE CONTROL SPIRES
HAD BEEN KNOCKED OUT
OF COMMISSION WHEN KEN LEFT,
BUT THIS MAKES ME THINK THEY
JUST MIGHT BE ACTIVE AGAIN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ EXHALING ]
HERE.
DIGMON AND I ARE GOING
TO GET BACK TO WORK
AND FINISH FIXING
THOSE WATER LINES.
HEY, HOW IS IT VEEMON AND I
END UP HAVING TO BABYSIT?
SOMEONE HAS TO
LOOK AFTER THEM.
THEY REALLY SEEM
TO LIKE YOU,
SO WE FIGURED
YOU'RE THE BEST CHOICE.
Voices: YAY!
SEE?
Davis: WAIT!
SEE YA!
HE-E-E-Y!
[ SIGHS ]
OH, BOY,
NOW WHAT DO I DO?
[ GROANS ]
ALL RIGHT, WATCH.
YOU CONTROL THE BALL LIKE THIS.
YOU GOT IT?
IT'S EASY.
HERE IT COMES, VEEMON!
GOT IT!
OKAY. NOW LET'S PLAY A GAME
SO YOU CAN TRY.
COME ON! GET THE BALL!
PASS IT, DAVIS!
I'M OPEN!
GO AFTER THAT BALL!
NICE! YOU'RE GETTING
THE HANG OF IT.
GREAT!
Davis: GO! GO! GO!
THAT'S IT! USE YOUR HEAD!
OUTSTANDING!
Kari: WE'RE BACK,
YOLEI.
T.K.: LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
I TOLD DAVIS
TO WATCH THE LITTLE ONES,
THOUGH I'M NOT SURE
WHO'S WATCHING WHO.
WHAT A GREAT IDEA.
THIS WAY, DAVIS GETS
TO BOSS AROUND SOMEONE ELSE
BESIDES JUST US.
SO, GIVE ME THE 4-1-1.
WERE YOU ABLE TO DIGIVOLVE?
NOPE. I THINK
THE CONTROL SPIRES
ARE WHAT'S KEEPING THEM
FROM DIGIVOLVING.
SO WE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO PROVE MY THEORY.
WHERE'S CODY, ANYWAY?
Digmon: BOY, THE EMPEROR
SURE LEFT A MESS HERE.
EVERYTHING'S BEEN BURIED.
WELL, WE GOT
A LOT TO DO.
I GUESS WE BETTER
GET STARTED, CODY.
CODY...
OH.
UH, YEAH, LET'S GET
TO WORK, DIGMON.
DIG IT!
HUH?
IT'S THUNDERBALLMON!
HE'S A HIGHLY CHARGED DIGIMON
WHO'S ELECTRIFYING,
BUT WHAT'S SHOCKING ABOUT
THIS PINT-SIZED POWERHOUSE
IS THAT HE PACKS
A 10-MILLION VOLT WALLOP!
[ GASPS ]
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
WHY IS HE ATTACKING US?
HE'S NOT BEING DIRECTED
BY A CONTROL SPIRE
OR WEARING A DARK RING.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
[ Thinking ] I'M NOT SURE
IF WE SHOULD FIGHT.
HUH?
HUH? HUH?
AAH!
[ Thinking ]
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
HE'S ATTACKING US
FOR NO REASON.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
HEY! WE HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING! STOP IT!
[ Thinking ] OH...
WE'RE IN BIG TROUBLE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
GRRAAH!
ARMADILLOMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANKYLOMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
THAT'S ENOUGH!
AAH!
YOU...DIGIVOLVED.
I'M ANKYLOMON,
A CHAMPION DIGIMON.
MY WHOLE BODY IS SURROUNDED
BY SUPER-STRENGTH STEEL.
I FLATTEN EVILDOERS
WITH MY MEGATON PRESS ATTACK,
AND THE IRON BALLS THAT SHOOT
FROM MY TAIL HAMMER
WILL DEFINITELY PUT A DENT
IN ANY ENEMY'S PLANS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY DID I DIGIVOLVE, CODY?
I DON'T KNOW.
NOW I'M REALLY CONFUSED.
VEEMON CAN'T DIGIVOLVE,
BUT YOU'RE
AT THE CHAMPION LEVEL.
ANYWAY, I THINK WE'D BETTER
GO ABOVE GROUND NOW.
RIGHT.
NOW YOU'D BETTER
TAKE COVER.
ANKYLOMON, DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE GOING TO FIGHT.
NO, I'M JUST GOING
TO DRIVE HIM AWAY.
AAH!
CODY!
HMM.
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
HERE.
THE ONE THAT CAUGHT ME --
WHO IS HE?
NEVER SEEN HIM BEFORE.
CODY!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
T.K.: JUST WHO IS THAT?
WE'RE BOTH FINE.
SO, CODY,
IS THAT DIGMON?
YES, ARMADILLOMON
AT THE CHAMPION LEVEL.
HE DIGIVOLVED?
UNBELIEVABLE.
WHO'S THAT DIGIMON
UP THERE?
NOBODY KNOWS.
THAT BIG GREEN ONE
HELPED US OUT.
IN FACT,
HE SAVED MY LIFE.
SPIKING STRIKE!
Davis: WHOA, WHAT DID
HE JUST DO TO THUNDERMON?
HE WAS...VAPORIZED.
Gatomon: LOOK!
UP THERE!
T.K.: KEN?
IT JUST CAN'T BE!
WHAT IS HE DOING
IN THE DIGIWORLD?
AAH!
WATCH OUT!
HA HA HA.
Davis: WORMMON?
T.K.: KEN'S BACK,
AND WORMMON CAN DIGIVOLVE?
SO WORMMON SAVED CODY,
DIDN'T HE?
I GUESS THAT'S RIGHT.
[ Thinking ] THIS REALLY
JUST DOESN'T ADD UP.
Davis: HERE COMES
THE BALL!
GOOD JOB. NOW ADVANCE
THE BALL TO THE GOAL.
THE GOAL IS THAT WAY!
T.K.: YOU'RE SO POPULAR!
HUH? JEALOUS?
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S MOVE IT!
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THIS.
HUH?
WHAT?
YOU KNOW THAT CONTROL SPIRE
THAT WAS UP ON THE RIDGE?
GUESS WHAT.
IT'S VANISHED.
Yolei: OH, NO, CODY'S RIGHT.
IT'S REALLY GONE.
HOW? WHEN?
MAYBE THAT'S WHY ARMADILLOMON
WAS ABLE TO DIGIVOLVE.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
Ken: ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
WORMMON?
WELL, I'VE BEEN BETTER.
I LET HER GET AWAY.
DON'T WORRY, MY FRIEND.
WE'LL HAVE ANOTHER CHANCE.
YOU'RE RIGHT, KEN.
NEXT TIME, I WON'T MISS.
Cody: HYAH!
[ Thinking ]
I STILL CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
WHAT WAS HIS ANGLE?
WHY DID KEN HELP ME?
[ GASPS ]
CODY, KENDO ISN'T JUST
DOING THE SAME MOVE
OVER AND OVER.
RIGHT.
[ PANTING ]
YOUR HEART, YOUR MIND,
YOUR TECHNIQUE --
YOU NEED TO BE SOFTER,
MORE FLUID.
SENSEI, YOU MEAN MORE LIKE
THAT LIQUID YOGURT?
HUH?
THAT'S ANOTHER WAY
TO LOOK AT THIS LESSON.
HA HA HA HA!
[ PANTING ]
WHY DID KEN HELP
THE DIGIDESTINED?
WHO IS THE MYSTERIOUS WOMAN?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."