Davis: I COULDN'T BELIEVE KEN
WENT WITH ARUKENIMON,
BUT AT LEAST HE HAD ME
TO RESCUE HIM.
DAEMON SHOWED UP,
AND THAT CREEPY OWIKAWA DUDE
WAS JUST GOING
TO HAND KEN OVER TO HIM.
I SPRANG INTO ACTION.
WE DIDN'T REALLY NEED THE HELP,
BUT I WAS GLAD WHEN
THE OTHERS FINALLY SHOWED UP.
TOOK THEM LONG ENOUGH.
DAEMON COULD OPEN DIGITAL PORTS
ANY TIME HE WANTED TO,
SO KARI SAID WE SHOULD
SEND HIM TO THE DARK OCEAN
INSTEAD OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
KEN HAD TO USE THE DARK POWER
STILL DEEP INSIDE HIM
TO OPEN THE GATE
AND BANISH DAEMON
FROM THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
NOW THAT'S
WHAT I CALL TEAMWORK.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Man: YES, SIR, WE'RE ORGANIZING
AND CLEANING.
ANY CLEANER, AND THE PLACE
WOULD BE A SOAP FACTORY.
I'VE ALREADY ORGANIZED
THAT DRAWER, SIR.
I'VE GOT THE PAPER CUTS
TO SHOW FOR IT, TOO.
SORRY. I JUST NEED
TO FIND SOMETHING.
I'LL GET THE BANDAGES.
BUT I'M ACTUALLY GOING TO MISS
THE OFFICE OVER THE HOLIDAYS.
IT'S ALWAYS SO NICE
AND QUIET.
FOUND IT!
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
THERE --
THIS IS THE GUY.
OH,
HE GIVES ME THE WILLIES.
IT IS HIM.
WELL, HE WAS AT WORK UNTIL
JUST A FEW DAYS AGO,
BUT YESTERDAY AND TODAY
HE DIDN'T SHOW UP AT ALL.
HE DIDN'T EVEN CALL IN
OR ANYTHING.
THANKS, DAD.
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF WE KEPT THIS PICTURE?
OF COURSE.
GO RIGHT AHEAD,
BUT DON'T DO ANYTHING
DANGEROUS, OKAY?
MM-HMM.
HMM, WHY DO I THINK
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO?
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE
AN ORDINARY PERSON.
YEAH? THEN WHY IS HE ABLE TO
CONTROL ARUKENIMON AND MUMMYMON?
I DON'T CARE
WHAT HE IS.
I JUST WANT
TO SHUT HIM DOWN.
AHH, MOUNT FUJI.
THIS WORLD CAN BE BEAUTIFUL,
BUT SOON I'LL CLAIM
MY TRUE PRIZE.
ARUKENIMON,
I BELIEVE THAT OPENS IN.
WELL,
IT DOES NOW.
HA HA HA HA!
IF YOU'RE THROUGH
PLAYING AROUND,
IT'S TIME
TO GET TO WORK.
THIS IS A CLASSIC CASE
OF MASS HALLUCINATION,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
BUILDINGS HAVE BEEN DESTROYED.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY
A GOVERNMENT CONSPIRACY
TO COVER UP A UFO CRASH.
WHAT I'M SAYING --
I MEAN, I'M JUST SAYING THAT
THE DESTRUCTION IS REAL,
BUT A MASS HALLUCINATION
CAUSED IT TO SEEM
THAT THE DESTRUCTION
WAS CAUSED BY MONSTERS.
THE GOVERNMENT GOT TO YOU, TOO,
DIDN'T IT?
OH, IF ONLY DIGIMON
WERE THIS DELUDED.
THE DIGITAL WORLD
WOULD FALL AT OUR FEET
LIKE A RIPE LITTLE PLUM.
TO THEM DIGIMON AND UFOs
ARE EXACTLY THE SAME THING.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING THEY'RE
AFRAID TO ADMIT EXISTS,
BUT THINK --
IF THERE'S SUCH
A COMMOTION NOW,
WAIT TILL ALL THOSE
DARK SPORES BEGIN TO BLOOM.
HA HA HA HA!
THERE WE GO.
I'M ALL DONE.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU'RE
DONE WITH YOUR HOMEWORK
FOR THE WHOLE
WINTER BREAK?
MM-HMM.
HONEY,
THAT'S AMAZING.
I'LL SAY IT IS.
CRAZY EVEN.
I MEAN,
HE WAS JUST RETURNED
FROM THAT WHOLE KIDNAPPING
INCIDENT LAST NIGHT.
THAT'S BECAUSE HE'S SUCH
A SMART LITTLE BOY.
YOU KNOW, THE PRESS
IS SURE TO SHOW UP AGAIN
TO TALK ABOUT
THE KIDNAPPING,
AND WE CAN GET
MORE ATTENTION
BY TELLING THEM
HOW SMART HE IS.
HON, MAYBE HE'LL BECOME
A MEDIA DARLING,
JUST LIKE THAT KEN ICHIJOUJI,
AND THEN WE'LL GET ON TV.
YOU BET.
THEN EVERYONE WILL KNOW
WE'RE THE PARENTS
OF A GENIUS.
[ Thinking ] INSECTS.
YES, THAT'S THE MAN,
ALL RIGHT.
OH,
HE GIVES ME THE WILLIES.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY
SAYS ABOUT HIM.
HEY, DIDN'T YOU NEED
TO BE SOMEPLACE?
YOU'RE RIGHT. FILL ME IN
WHEN I GET BACK, OKAY?
NOW FEEL FREE
TO MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME.
All: THANKS.
SEE YOU LATER.
OH, WAIT. HERE.
T.K.: LOOKS LIKE MOM HAS DONE
SOME INVESTIGATING OF HER OWN.
HUH?
DIDN'T YOU KNOW T.K.'S MOM
IS A NEWSPAPER REPORTER?
REALLY?
YEAH, AND LOOK.
WOW! UH, WHAT IS IT?
OOH,
IS IT A GROCERY LIST?
NO, GOOFY.
IT'S THE NAMES AND ADDRESSES
OF THE KIDNAPPED KIDS.
YOUR MOM DOES GOOD WORK,
T.K.
WE'VE GOT TO SAVE THEM ALL
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU CAN COUNT ME IN.
WE CAN'T ALLOW
THOSE CHILDREN
TO BECOME DRAWN INTO EVIL
THE WAY I WAS.
RIGHT. ALL THOSE KIDS
ARE DEPENDING ON US.
All: YEAH!
HEY, I DON'T MEAN
TO CAUSE TROUBLE,
BUT JUST WHAT IS
THE PLAN ANYWAY?
WELL, UM...
LET'S SPLIT UP
AND GO MEET WITH THOSE KIDS.
IF WE ACT QUICKLY,
MAYBE WE CAN STOP
THE DARK SPORES FROM GROWING.
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S GO.
THAT NORIKO GIRL SHOULD
BE HOME ANY TIME NOW, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
GUYS, ISN'T THAT HER, LIKE,
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US?
OH, YEAH.
SHE DOESN'T LOOK SO EVIL
PLAYING WITH THAT CAT.
GET AWAY FROM ME.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
[ CAT MEOWS ]
SHE KICKED IT!
I GUESS SHE IS EVIL,
HUH?
YEAH. MAYBE IT'S NOT EVEN
WORTH TALKING TO HER.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE DARK SPORE
HAS ALREADY TAKEN HOLD.
WE HAVE TO AT LEAST TRY.
[ Thinking ] I DON'T EVEN
LIKE TO FIGHT DIGIMON.
WHAT WILL WE DO IF WE'RE
FORCED TO FIGHT OTHER KIDS?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
Woman: NO. NOW GO AWAY
AND DON'T COME BACK!
WAIT, MA'AM.
JUST LISTEN FOR A MINUTE.
MAN, HOW DO PEOPLE
GET ANY ENCYCLOPEDIAS SOLD?
SORRY, GUYS. I TRIED.
I KNOW, DAVIS.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
SHE GOT ANGRY.
YEAH.
SHE NEEDS SOME CATNIP.
WELL,
LET'S TRY THE NEXT ONE.
INSECTS.
STUPID LITTLE
MEANINGLESS BUGS.
THEY NEED TO BE SQUASHED!
OKAY, I'LL THROW IN
SOME OYSTERS, BROCCOLI,
A QUART OF BUTTERMILK,
AND JUST A DASH
OF VINEGAR.
[ HUMMING ]
WHY DO PEOPLE
FIND THIS COLD WET GUNK PRETTY?
DO YOU THINK IT'LL CAUSE
ANY PROBLEMS TOMORROW?
WELL, I SUPPOSE ANYTHING
IS POSSIBLE, ARUKENIMON.
GO PUT THE SNOW CHAINS
ON THE TIRES.
WHAT?
WHY SHOULD I?
BECAUSE
YOU'RE ANNOYING ME.
FINE.
"BECAUSE YOU'RE ANNOYING ME."
HUH?
WAS THAT A SHOOTING STAR?
KEN, I KNOW YOU'RE GOING
TO HATE HEARING THIS,
BUT I REALLY DON'T THINK
WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO REMOVE THE DARK SPORES
FROM THOSE KIDNAPPED KIDS.
I'M THINKING THAT OWIKAWA
IS PROBABLY THE ONLY PERSON
THAT CAN EXTRACT THEM,
BUT WE MAY BE ABLE
TO USE THAT TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
HE'S PROBABLY GOT
SOMETHING SPECIFIC PLANNED
AND WILL COME FOR THEM
SOONER OR LATER, SO...
SO IF WE WATCH THEM,
WE'LL CATCH OWIKAWA.
RIGHT.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE CAN ASK TAI AND THE OTHERS
TO HELP US OUT, TOO.
I'M SORRY, KEN.
I KNOW YOU'D HOPED WE COULD
SAVE THOSE KIDS BEFORE --
YOU REALLY DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'LL BE FINE.
MM-HMM.
YOU EVER NOT GET MAIL?
IT'S FROM MY BROTHER.
ALL RIGHT! LET'S GET STARTED
ON THIS PLAN, GUYS.
Black Wargreymon:
THEY ARE NEARBY. I CAN SENSE IT.
PERHAPS NOW
I WILL FINALLY FIND
THE ANSWERS I SEEK.
[ SNORING ]
Mummymon: NO,
IT'S MY TEDDY BEAR! MINE!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU --
YOU CAN'T HAVE IT!
HEY, YOU LAZY BONES,
WAKE UP!
WHAT?
WE HAVE A VISITOR.
FIND OUT WHO.
TEDDY BEAR?
[ ALL GROANING ]
[ GASPS ]
IT'S BLACK WARGREYMON.
OH, NO.
OH, YES.
OKAY, EVERYBODY HAS GOT
THEIR ASSIGNMENTS
ABOUT WHO THEY'RE
SUPPOSED TO FOLLOW.
MAKE SURE YOU
STICK CLOSE TO THEM.
WE DON'T WANT OWIKAWA SNEAKING
IN WHEN WE'RE NOT LOOKING.
WHILE WE'RE FOLLOWING
THOSE KIDS,
TAI AND KARI ARE GOING
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
OKAY, SEE YOU SOON.
LOOK AT ALL THIS DESTRUCTION.
ANY IDEA WHAT CAUSED IT?
NO.
HEY, TAI, KARI.
SORRY TO CALL YOU INTO
THE DIGITAL WORLD LIKE THIS,
BUT YOU'RE IN REAL
SERIOUS DANGER.
YOU-KNOW-WHO
IS UP TO SOMETHING.
TWITCH MY TAIL.
YOU DON'T MEAN --
NOT BLACK WARGREYMON?
Both: MM-HMM.
REMEMBER WHEN AZULONGMON
GAVE UP SOME OF HIS POWER
TO HELP US FIGHT
IN THE REAL WORLD?
WELL, WHEN GENNAI GAVE
THAT POWER TO ALL OF US,
THE DEFENSES OF THE DIGITAL
WORLD WERE WEAKENED.
WITH THE BALANCE
THROWN OFF HERE,
THERE'S NOT MUCH
THAT CAN STAND IN THE WAY
OF BLACK WARGREYMON.
Tai: I GUESS WE'VE GOT NO CHOICE
BUT TO TRY AND FIND A WAY.
HEY, LOOK!
WHAT IS IT?
LOOKS LIKE MOUNT FUJI.
THAT'S BECAUSE
IT IS MOUNT FUJI.
DO YOU MEAN
THAT BLACK WARGREYMON
IS IN THE REAL WORLD?
THAT'S WHAT
AZULONGMON TOLD US.
WE KNEW WE HAD TO
CALL YOU GUYS.
BUT WE DON'T HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO DEFEAT HIM.
AGUMON GOT MORE POWER
FROM AZULONGMON,
BUT THERE WASN'T ENOUGH POWER
FOR ANYONE ELSE.
UNH-UNH.
DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE UP TO FIGHTING
BLACK WARGREYMON, BUDDY?
IF HE REALLY,
REALLY WANTS TO.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S GO FIND HIM,
GUYS.
BE CAREFUL
WITH BLACK WARGREYMON,
BUT YOU CAN'T LET HIM WIN!
SO WE MEET AGAIN.
AND THIS TIME
WE'RE READY FOR YOU.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
READY TO BE DEFEATED AGAIN,
YOU MEAN?
SO THIS IS THE INFAMOUS
BLACK WARGREYMON.
JUST WHAT DO YOU HOPE
TO ACCOMPLISH HERE?
I WISH TO LOOK UPON THE FACE
OF MY CREATOR.
HA HA HA HA.
YOU'VE COME ALL THIS WAY
TO SEE WHAT YOU'VE
ALREADY SEEN THEN.
I GAVE YOU LIFE FROM JUST
THE TINY HAIRS ON MY HEAD.
PERHAPS,
BUT WHO GAVE YOU LIFE?
Both: HUH?
AND WHO IS YOUR CREATOR,
MUMMYMON?
Mummymon:
OH, WELL, IT, UM...
IT WAS ME.
Both: HUH?
I MADE BOTH OF THESE DIGIMON
BY TURNING MY DNA INTO DATA,
SO YOU SEE,
BLACK WARGREYMON,
I AM THE CREATOR
YOU'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR.
THEN I AM A PRODUCT
OF THE REAL WORLD,
NOT THE DIGITAL ONE.
INTERESTING.
YES, I THINK YOU'VE GOTTEN
WHAT YOU CAME FOR, HAVEN'T YOU?
SO NOW LEAVE US.
IT'S ALL BEGINNING
TO MAKE SENSE TO ME NOW.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR ANSWERS
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD --
TRYING TO FIND THE MEANING
OF MY EXISTENCE,
BUT HAVE BEEN ABLE TO FIND
NOTHING TO EASE MY PAIN,
AND NOW I KNOW WHY.
I WAS CREATED FROM YOU,
JUST LIKE ARUKENIMON
AND MUMMYMON WERE.
WE'RE A PART
OF THE REAL WORLD --
FOREIGN
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WE DO NOT BELONG THERE.
IF YOU'RE DONE PHILOSOPHIZING,
THEN GOODBYE.
I'LL LEAVE
AS SOON AS I'M DONE HERE.
FOREIGN OBJECTS
MUST BE ELIMINATED.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M NOT A FOREIGN OBJECT.
BUT YOU ARE. YOU BELONG IN
NEITHER THE DIGITAL WORLD
NOR THE REAL WORLD.
YOU UPSET THE BALANCE OF BOTH.
Mummymon:
THIS GUY IS TALKING CRAZY.
DO YOU WANT ME TO, UH,
TAKE CARE OF HIM FOR YOU,
BOSS?
A FOREIGN OBJECT?
I GIVE YOU LIFE
AND THIS IS HOW YOU REPAY ME?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
AAH!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
YOU --
I REMEMBER YOU!
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
THERE IS NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
HEY, LOOK OUT!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
AGUMON
WARP DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
WARP DIGIVOLVE.
WARGREYMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
IT'S GOING TO BE
A GOOD FIGHT.
MAYBE WE SHOULD STAY.
GATOMON, STOP HIM --
QUICK!
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
GATOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
NEFERTIMON --
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WHY DO YOU PROTECT HIM?
BECAUSE WITHOUT OWIKAWA,
WE'LL NEVER GET THE DARK SPORES
OUT OF THOSE KIDS.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
THEY'LL STAY IN THERE FOREVER
IF WE LET YOU DESTROY HIM.
THEN YOU SHOULD'VE
STOPPED HIM,
NOT ATTACKED ME!
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
HURTING TAI!
STOP HER.
SNAKE BANDAGE!
CAT'S EYE BEAM!
WE'D BETTER CALL THE OTHERS.
RIGHT.
STOP. DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT?
WE SHOULD BE
WORKING TOGETHER.
NEVER! PTERA-DESTROYER!
NO! WATCH OUT!
ROSETTA STONE!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
WHEN WE COULD BE FRIENDS?
FRIENDSHIP IS WEAKNESS.
FIGHTING, STRUGGLE --
THAT IS MY LIFE.
BUT IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE THAT WAY.
ENOUGH!
THERE IS NO NEED
FOR TWO WARGREYMONS
IN THIS WORLD.
EITHER YOU GO...
OR I GO.
NEVER FEAR,
THE GANG IS ALL HERE!
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
HEY, WHERE IS DAVIS AND KEN?
THEY WENT AHEAD
TO CUT OFF TRAFFIC.
JUST A DETOUR, FOLKS.
NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
YEP, JUST A COUPLE
OF BIG DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIRECTING TRAFFIC.
YOU HEARD WHAT
THE BIG MONSTER SAID, FOLKS.
I JUST THOUGHT
OF SOMETHING.
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT HAPPENS IF THE MILITARY
BASE GETS INVOLVED IN THIS?
DON'T WORRY.
CODY AND THE OTHERS
CAN TAKE CARE OF THEM.
ROCK CRACKER!
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD,
SOLDIER BOYS!
BLAST RINGS!
CAT'S EYE BEAM!
MAYBE I SHOULD DRIVE.
FINE.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
IT'S THREE ON ONE OUT HERE.
LET'S EVEN THE ODDS.
SPIDER THREAD!
SNAKE BANDAGE!
HA HA HA.
TAKE THAT, BRATS!
[ GASPS ]
YOU CAN'T GET AWAY!
GO GET THEM,
PAILDRAMON!
HYAH!
OH, NO!
HE'S ESCAPING!
PTERA-DESTROYER!
THEY'RE HEADING
TOWARD THE BASE.
YEAH, BUT SHOULD WE STOP THEM
OR GO AFTER OWIKAWA?
WHICH ONE
IS IT GOING TO BE, GUYS?
OH, MAN, I DON'T KNOW!
I GUESS
IT SHOULD BE THE BASE.
LET'S GO THEN.
PAILDRAMON
MEGA-DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
IMPERIALDRAMON!
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
THERE THEY GO!
COME ON,
WE CAN STILL CATCH THEM.
[ ALL SCREAM ]
NOW YOU SHALL FACE
YOUR DOOM!
NO!
IMPERIALDRAMON
MODE CHANGE TO FIGHTER FORM!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
UNHAND ME...
OR FEEL MY WRATH!
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE.
WHY IS HE SO EAGER
TO FIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IF WE FIGHT HERE,
AT LEAST NO ONE
WILL BE HURT.
SO BE IT.
PTERA-DESTROYER!
PTERA-FORCE!
POSITRON LASER!
WHOA!
OH,
THWARTED AT EVERY TURN!
OUR ONLY CHANCE IS TO RUN.
COME ON!
WATCH OUT, EVERYBODY!
HEY, LOOK AT THE SALE PRICES
ON THOSE JACKETS!
WILL YOU BE QUIET?
WITH ALL THESE PEOPLE AROUND,
I CAN'T ATTACK.
I CAN.
[ GROANING ]
HAWKMON!
SPEAK TO ME.
SO DID WE GET HIM?
NO. HE GOT AWAY.
JUST WHEN WE
ALMOST HAD HIM.
T.K.: IT'S THE POLICE.
WE BETTER GET GOING.
I'M SURPRISED
YOU COULD DEFEAT ME --
EVEN TWO ON ONE,
THOUGH I ALMOST WISH
YOU HAD DESTROYED ME COMPLETELY.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE AFTER?
WHAT?
YOU MEAN THIS WHOLE TIME
WE'VE BEEN CHASING YOU AROUND --
WATCHING YOU BLOW UP
EVERYTHING BLOW-UPABLE,
YOU'VE JUST WANTED TO FIND
SOMETHING TO DESTROY YOU?
DON'T YOU HAVE ANYTHING BETTER
TO DO WITH YOUR FREE TIME?
HMM.
MY LIFE HAS NO MEANING.
POOR, POOR PITIFUL ME.
I KNOW
ALL ABOUT SELF-PITY.
WHEN KEN WAS
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
HE TREATED ME
LIKE FISH BAIT.
I ALMOST STARTED TO BELIEVE
THE AWFUL THINGS HE SAID,
BUT DEEP INSIDE
I HAD FAITH
THAT SOMEDAY THE REAL KEN
WOULD COME BACK TO ME.
I JUST KEPT TRYING
TO GET THROUGH TO HIM.
I DIDN'T GIVE UP,
AND NEITHER CAN YOU.
EVEN IF YOUR LIFE
IS ALL FIGHTING AND STRUGGLE,
IT CAN STILL HAVE MEANING.
I'VE HAD TO FIGHT ALL MY LIFE,
BUT I'VE BELIEVED
IN WHAT I WAS FIGHTING FOR.
I THINK IT'S THAT BELIEF,
NOT THE FIGHTING,
THAT HAS GIVEN
MY LIFE MEANING.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THE TROUBLE
TAI WOULD GET INTO WITHOUT ME?
IF ALL YOU'VE GOT
IN YOUR LIFE IS LEMONS,
MAKE LEMON PIE!
HEY, I'M HUNGRY.
HMM.
AND YOUR LIFE DOESN'T,
YOU KNOW, HAVE TO BE FILLED
WITH A WHOLE BUNCH
OF INCREDIBLY AMAZING EVENTS
TO BE SPECIAL.
BELIEVE ME,
SOME OF THE BEST TIMES I'VE HAD
ARE JUST EATING AND SLEEPING
AND HANGING OUT WITH MY FRIENDS,
AND THE THING IS,
WE WOULD ALL BE YOUR FRIENDS
IF YOU'D JUST GIVE US
THE CHANCE TO BE.
HE'S RIGHT.
LOOK AT KEN.
HE NEVER THOUGHT
HE COULD HAVE FRIENDS,
AND NOW HE HAS
LOTS OF THEM.
YOU JUST NEED TO LIGHTEN UP
A LITTLE. GIVE US A CHANCE.
PLEASE DON'T GO.
DON'T YOU WANT SOME PIE?
THIS IS ALL SO FOREIGN TO ME.
I MUST THINK ON IT.
ARE YOU SURE?
I THANK YOU
FOR YOUR ADVICE.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
PERHAPS IT IS TIME
TO PUT ASIDE MY WARRIOR WAYS.
THEY HAVE PROVIDED ME
FEW ANSWERS,
AND MAYBE ONE DAY
WE COULD EVEN BE FRIENDS.
I HOPE SO,
BLACK WARGREYMON.
I HOPE SO.
WILL BLACK WARGREYMON
FIND THE ANSWERS HE SEEKS
AND JOIN THE DIGIDESTINED
IN THEIR QUEST TO DEFEAT
THE FORCES OF DARKNESS?
KEEP WATCHING "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS" TO FIND OUT.