TAI WANTED TO GET BACK TO
THE DIGIWORLD TO SAVE AGUMON.
YOLEI STAYED BEHIND.
KEN COULDN'T CONTROL
AGUMON WITH THE DARK RING,
SO HE MADE HIM DIGIVOLVE
INTO SKULLGREYMON.
KEN MADE THE DARK RING
MORE POWERFUL
BY TURNING IT
INTO THE DARK SPIRAL.
WORMMON RELEASED AGUMON.
HE WANTED KEN TO USE HIM
ON HIS EXPERIMENTS,
BUT N WOULDN'T LISTEN.
WHEN AGUMON REUNITED WITH TAI
AND THE REST OF US,
KEN SHOWED UP AND WON A BATTLE
AND REGAINED CONTROL OF AGUMON.
TAI WAS DEVASTATED.
YOLEI ARRIVED WITH MATT
WHO GOT TAI TO STOP
FEELING SORRY FOR HIMSELF.
WE HEADED OFF
TO FIND AGUMON.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
AAH!
NOW THAT I'VE GOT MY AIR FORCE
AND MY ARMOR,
I'M CONQUERING MORE
AND MORE TERRITORIES EACH DAY.
WITH THESE NEW AND IMPROVED
DARK RINGS,
NOT ONLY WILL I CONTROL
METALGREYMON,
BUT ALL OTHER DIGIMON
AS WELL.
AAH!
YOU'RE READY FOR A FIGHT NOW,
TOO, AREN'T YOU?
LET'S GO!
[ Gasps ]
IT'S TENTOMON.
ALL ABOARD!
I JUST LOVE RIDING TRAINS.
WHERE'S THE DINING CAR?
AN E-MAIL FROM IZZY.
HAS HE FOUND THEM YET?
APPARENTLY, KEN AND METALGREYMON
HAVE BEEN SEEN SOUTH OF HERE.
WE'RE ON
THE RIGHT TRACK.
WELL, TECHNICALLY, MATT,
WE'RE ON THE ONLY TRACK.
ALL RIGHT, DIGIDESTINED,
THIS TIME WE'LL
GET AGUMON BACK FOR SURE.
YEAH. THERE'S NO WAY THAT
KEN CAN STOP ALL OF US.
UH, BUT, JUST IN CASE,
TENTOMON, I NEED YOUR HELP.
NOW? I WAS GOING
TO HAVE MY SHELL WAXED.
I WANT YOU TO GO
IN SEARCH FOR GARURUMON.
GARURUMON, HUH? OKAY.
I'LL BE BACK IN A FLASH.
HUH?
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SAYING
YOU'RE PLANNING FOR US
TO FIGHT METALGREYMON?
WITH ALL OF US TOGETHER,
I THINK WE STAND A CHANCE.
THERE ARE JUST SOME THINGS
THAT HAVE TO BE DONE.
AM I RIGHT, TAI?
YEAH.
I'M NOT SO SURE, GUYS.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
WE'LL BE ABLE TO DEFEAT
KEN AND METALGREYMON?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
WE CAN'T?
WHO ASKED YOU?
I'M SPEAKING
FROM EXPERIENCE.
WE HAVE TO FIGHT
BECAUSE IF WE DON'T,
WE'LL NEVER SAVE AGUMON.
WHAT ARE YOU
SO AFRAID OF ANYWAY, DAVIS?
WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT BEING AFRAID?
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO SEE AGUMON GET HURT.
NO ONE SAID
WE HAVE TO HURT HIM.
WE HAVE TO GET RID
OF THAT DARK RING.
AND HOW DO YOU PROPOSE
WE REMOVE IT,
ESPECIALLY WITHOUT
HURTING AGUMON?
ANY BRIGHT IDEAS
UNDER THAT FANCY HAT?
AT LEAST I'M TRYING,
GOGGLE HEAD,
AND DON'T MAKE FUN
OF MY HAT!
THAT'S IT!
STOP FIGHTING.
DO I HAVE TO SEPARATE YOU TWO
LIKE A COUPLE OF CHILDREN?
LET THEM FIGHT.
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHEN MATT AND I WERE YOUNGER,
WE FOUGHT A LOT, TOO,
BUT IF WE HADN'T, WE NEVER
WOULD'VE BECOME GOOD FRIENDS,
SO JUST LET THEM
FIGHT IT OUT OF THEIR SYSTEMS.
LEAVE IT TO BOYS
TO THINK THEY HAVE TO FIGHT
TO BECOME FRIENDS.
THE BEST WAY TO MAKE FRIENDS
IS OVER A GAME OF CHECKERS.
SOUNDS GREAT.
I GET THE WINNER.
BUT FOR NOW WHAT WE NEED
TO DO IS CATCH UP TO KEN.
EVERYBODY, BLOW!
GARURUMON!
OH, GARURUMON!
WHERE COULD HE BE?
HUH. THAT'S EITHER THE BIGGEST
SUNDIAL I'VE EVER SEEN,
OR IT'S ONE OF THE DIGIMON
EMPEROR'S CONTROL SPIRES.
HOLD YOUR HORSES.
WHAT'S THAT?
A SQUADRON OF KUWAGAMON,
AND THEY'RE ALL BEING CONTROLLED
BY THOSE DARK RINGS.
I'M DEFINITELY GOING
TO NEED SOME BACKUP.
I'VE GOT TO FIND GARURUMON.
CAN'T THIS THING
GO ANY FASTER?
HEY, EVERYBODY,
LOOK AT THIS.
MY D-3 HAS FOUND A DIGI-EGG.
WELL, DON'T JUST SIT THERE.
HIT THE BRAKES.
All: WHOA!
WHO COULD'VE CARVED THAT?
SOMEONE WITH A REALLY
BIG CHISEL.
IT LOOKS LIKE
MY CREST OF FRIENDSHIP,
BUT WHY WOULD SOMEONE
GO TO THE TROUBLE
OF CARVING THAT
INTO THE SIDE OF A WALL?
I THINK
THE EGG IS IN THERE.
BIGFOOT WAS HERE.
WHAT'S DOWN THERE?
LOOKS LIKE A FLIP-FLOP
WITH A BENT NAIL IN IT.
HAS EVERYONE HAD
A TETANUS SHOT?
IT'S GOT
THAT SAME SYMBOL.
IT DEFINITELY HAS
THE CREST OF FRIENDSHIP ON IT.
I WONDER IF IT'S MEANT
FOR YOU, MATT.
MAYBE IT'S MEANT FOR THE ONE
WITH THE MOST FRIENDS.
WITH THE FEWEST FRIENDS.
SOMEONE SHOULD PICK IT UP.
WHAT COULD HAPPEN?
WELL, IT COULD BE A TRAP
SET UP BY THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
I DON'T THINK
IT WOULD BE BOOBY TRAPPED.
AFTER ALL, IT'S EMBLAZONED
WITH THE CREST OF FRIENDSHIP.
THEN I THINK
YOU SHOULD GO FOR IT, MATT.
WISH ME LUCK --
JUST IN CASE.
[ GRUNTING ]
NO LUCK.
CODY, WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE IT A TRY?
OKAY.
[ GRUNTING ]
I SHOULD'VE HAD
A BIGGER BREAKFAST.
ALL RIGHT, TAI,
IT'S YOUR TURN.
OKAY.
All: LIFT, TAI, LIFT.
LIFT, TAI, LIFT.
OH.
ALL RIGHT,
WHICH ONE OF YOU IS NEXT?
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
I THINK I'M DONE.
ME, TOO.
AAH! OH!
I THINK YOU GUYS ARE GOING
ABOUT THIS ALL WRONG.
YOU THINK YOU CAN LIFT IT?
YEAH. YOU JUST
HAVE TO USE PHYSICS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU SEE, IN PHYSICS
THERE'S EQUILIBRIUM --
WHEN YOU HAVE TWO LIBRIUMS
THAT WEIGH THE SAME,
THEY'RE EQUILIBRIUM.
THAT MAKES
PERFECT SENSE TO ME.
HUH?
UM, YOU KNOW, TAI,
I WAS JUST MAKING THAT STUFF UP.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT PHYSICS.
I USUALLY LEAVE ALL THAT STUFF
UP TO PROFESSORS
AND SCIENTISTS AND IZZY.
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D TAKE ME SERIOUSLY.
OH, I'M SICK OF ALL
YOUR BLABBERING, DAVIS.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HASN'T TRIED YET,
SO JUST GET IN THE HOLE!
YEAH, LIFT THAT DIGI-EGG UP
SO WE CAN GET OUT OF HERE!
OKAY,
THIS SHOULDN'T BE TOO HARD.
1...
2...3.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I GIVE UP.
AAH!
WHAT'S THAT TERRIBLE NOISE?
IT'S HURTING MY EARS!
SOMETHING'S FLYING.
[ BUZZING ]
DEADLY STING!
WATCH OUT!
WHOA!
POISONED STINGERS!
PATAMON!
IT'S FLYMON.
THE ONLY THING WORSE
THAN HIS DEADLY STING ATTACK
IS THE NOISE HE MAKES
WHEN ATTACKING.
WHEN I HEAR HIM COMING I USUALLY
DIG A HOLE UNTIL HE BLOWS OVER.
LET'S DO IT!
RIGHT, PAL.
DIGI-ARMOR -- ENERGIZE!
VEEMON ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE!
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
FIRE ROCKET!
HAWKMON!
RIGHT.
DIGI-ARMOR -- ENERGIZE!
HAWKMON ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE!
HALSEMON --
THE WINGS OF LOVE!
TEMPEST WING!
AAH!
HERE HE COMES AGAIN!
[ BUZZING ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
HUH?
PATAMON IS GONE!
WHERE DID HE GO?
DID HE RUN AWAY?
NO. LOOK UP. THERE HE IS!
HELP, T.K., HELP!
HANG ON, PATAMON,
WE'LL SAVE YOU!
BUT HOW?
HE'S GETTING AWAY!
PATAMON!
[ PANTING ]
I THINK WE'RE GAINING.
OH!
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
METALGREYMON!
T.K., DAVIS,
GET OUT OF THERE!
HA HA HA HA HA!
[ ALL GRUNT ]
HERE'S YOUR NEW PLAY TOY,
YOUR EVILNESS.
PATAMON!
PUT HIM DOWN!
NO. I'M JUST GETTING
STARTED WITH HIM.
HE'S GOT MORE DARK RINGS.
WHAT DOES HE HAVE PLANNED?
YOU CAN BE SURE
IT'S SOMETHING BAD.
WHEN I PUT THIS
ON YOUR LITTLE FRIEND HERE,
I WILL HAVE
COMPLETE CONTROL OVER HIM,
AND I CAN MAKE HIM DO ANYTHING
I WANT. DO YOU HEAR THAT?
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU DO MY
LAUNDRY ONE PIECE AT A TIME --
I'LL NEVER LET YOU
GET AWAY WITH IT!
DON'T INTERRUPT ME WHILE
I'M PLANNING MY EVIL DEEDS!
[ Growls ] FIRE!
HOLD IT, FLAMEDRAMON!
YOU MIGHT ACCIDENTALLY MISS
AND HIT PATAMON!
I'M SUCH A HOTHEAD.
SORRY.
WE HAVE TO SEPARATE PATAMON
AND THE EMPEROR.
I DON'T SEE HOW WE CAN.
WE'VE GOT TO TRY.
OH, YEAH? HOW?
BY USING YOU AS BAIT.
ME? WHY DO I
HAVE TO BE THE ONE?
WE HAVE TO USE SOME KIND
OF BAIT WE CAN DO WITHOUT.
WE CAN EASILY
DO WITHOUT YOUR HAT!
NOW IS A GOOD TIME TO REMEMBER
THE CREST OF FRIENDSHIP, OKAY?
I'D LOVE TO SEE
HOW THIS TURNS OUT,
BUT I'VE GOT TO RUN.
I HAVE A FEW CHORES
TO TAKE CARE OF,
LIKE TAKING OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE GOING TO
LET YOU USE PATAMON TO HELP YOU.
THAT GOES FOR AGUMON,
TOO.
THAT'S REALLY FUNNY
BECAUSE I DON'T REMEMBER
ASKING FOR PERMISSION.
YOU REALLY SHOULD HAVE
FLYMON TRIM HIS NAILS BACK.
JUST HOLD STILL.
IN A FEW SECONDS
YOU WON'T REMEMBER A THING,
EXCEPT WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE MY SLAVE.
HA HA HA HA!
[ GROANING ]
PATAMON!
GET DOWN!
[ GROWLS ]
HUH?
NICE GOING.
GARURUMON,
YOU CAME JUST IN TIME.
T.K.!
PATAMON,
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
KIND OF LIKE A BIG PIECE
OF DENTAL FLOSS,
BUT OTHER THAN THAT,
I'M FINE.
I HAVE TO
HAND IT TO T.K. --
HE REALLY RISKED HIMSELF
TO SAVE PATAMON.
WHAT A FRIEND.
WOULD YOU TRY TO PROTECT ME
IF I WAS IN DANGER, DAVIS?
HUH? UM, MAYBE.
MAYBE? MAYBE!
WHAT ABOUT DEFINITELY?
OH, YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO MAKE ME CRY.
IF YOU REALLY WANT A TEST
OF YOUR FRIENDSHIP,
I'LL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO GIVE YOU ONE.
PREPARE FOR THE FIGHT
OF YOUR LIFE! METALGREYMON!
AAH!
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM,
METALGREYMON!
DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
I'M YOUR FRIEND.
GARURUMON AND I
ARE GOING TO TRY
TO GET THOSE RINGS
OFF METALGREYMON'S ARM.
[ GROWLS ]
SQUASH THEM LIKE A BUG!
GARURUMON,
THAT WAS CLOSE.
WE'VE GOT TO ATTACK HIM
WITH ALL OUR STRENGTH.
I'M AFRAID
OF HURTING METALGREYMON.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
IF WE DON'T USE OUR FULL POWER,
HE'LL CRUSH US LIKE GRAPES.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, TAI?
GO GET HIM!
BUT, MATT --
IT'S TIME TO CALL IN
THE CAVALRY.
DIGI-ARMOR -- ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER!
DIGI-ARMOR -- ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
DATAMON ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
NEFERTIMON --
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT!
GOLD RUSH!
ROSETTA STONE!
TEMPEST WING!
CAREFUL.
YOU'LL HURT HIM!
SORRY.
YOU DID WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE GETTING ANNOYING.
WHOA!
HOWLING BLASTER!
AAH!
METALGREYMON,
I'M SORRY.
WE'RE ONLY DOING THIS
OUT OF FRIENDSHIP.
DAVIS, HELP US.
COME ON. AREN'T YOU GOING
TO HELP THEM FIGHT?
I JUST CAN'T DO IT.
THERE'S A CHANCE
I'LL HURT METALGREYMON.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP.
AAH!
VEEMON! OH, NO!
DAVIS,
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT.
HOW CAN YOU JUST STAND THERE
AND LET HIM TRY TO HURT ME?
LAY OFF. WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I DON'T WANT TO HURT ANYBODY.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
IT'S ABOUT THE THINGS
YOU HAVE TO DO FOR FRIENDSHIP.
HUH? FRIENDSHIP?
AGUMON, DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY
ONE MORE TIME
TO REMOVE THOSE RINGS
FROM YOUR ARM.
MATT, GARURUMON,
DO YOUR BEST.
[ GROWLS ]
I GOT YOU, VEEMON.
I OWE YOU ONE.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M KEEPING TRACK.
VEEMON, YOU OKAY?
HE IS,
BUT NO THANKS TO YOU.
PATAMON RISKED HIS LIFE
TO SAVE HIM,
AND ALL YOU DID
WAS STAND THERE AND WATCH.
T.K., I...
VEEMON,
I'M YOUR FRIEND!
THIS IS NEW.
HIS DIGIVICE IS RESPONDING
TO THE NEW DIGI-EGG.
WHAT'S IT DOING?
LOOK -- IT STOPPED
RIGHT IN FRONT YOU.
TAKE IT.
IT'S YOUR DIGI-EGG
OF FRIENDSHIP, DAVIS.
MY DIGI-EGG OF FRIENDSHIP?
DAVIS ALREADY HAS
THE DIGI-EGG OF COURAGE,
SO HOW CAN HE
NOW HAVE ANOTHER ONE?
I THINK THAT MEANS
THAT VEEMON CAN BECOME
TWICE AS POWERFUL.
WE CAN WIN NOW.
HEY, THAT'S COOL.
HEY,
LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
DIGI-ARMOR -- ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS... ♪
RAYDRAMON --
THE STORM OF FRIENDSHIP!
[ GROWLS ]
I AM RAYDRAMON.
AS VEEMON, I USED
THE DIGI-EGG OF FRIENDSHIP
TO ARMOR DIGIVOLVE.
MY BLUE THUNDER
AND ELECTRIC BITE ATTACKS
ANNIHILATE MY ENEMIES.
FINALLY, SOMEONE WHO CAN
STAND UP TO THE EMPEROR --
RAYDRAMON!
[ GASPS ]
HA HA. SHOW THEM
WHO'S IN CHARGE HERE!
[ GROWLS ]
BLUE THUNDER!
GOT YOU!
IT'S NO USE.
IT WON'T COME OFF.
HA HA HA.
YOUR WEAK ATTEMPTS
MAKE ME LAUGH.
HA HA HA.
GIVE UP YET?
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY
TO GET THROUGH
TO METALGREYMON SOMEHOW.
DON'T WORRY, TAI.
WE WON'T GIVE UP.
WE'LL GET HIM BACK FOR YOU,
RIGHT, GARURUMON?
RIGHT!
DAVIS,
THIS IS A TEAM EFFORT.
WE'RE BOTH GOING TO ATTACK
HIM AT THE SAME TIME.
WE NEED YOU.
I'M NOT SURE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO THINGS
THE RIGHT WAY.
HOW CAN I?
WE'LL FIGHT TOGETHER.
ALL THIS TIME
I'VE BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT'S BEST FOR ME
AND NOT THE TEAM.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
LET'S GO -- NOW!
RIGHT. RAYDRAMON,
ARE YOU READY?
LET'S GIVE IT
OUR BEST SHOT.
♪ DIGIMON --
WE FIGHT TO WIN ♪
COME ON, GUYS.
♪ WE FIGHT TO WIN ♪
HOWLING BLASTER!
AAH!
♪ WE GOT THE POWER ♪
♪ WE GOT THE STRENGTH,
YEAH ♪
♪ WE KNOW
IT'S GOT TO GIVE ♪
[ ALL GASP ]
LOOK -- IT'S OFF!
WHAT?
♪ WE'LL WIN THE VICTORY ♪
I'M SORRY
WE ATTACKED YOU, AGUMON.
I'M SORRY, TOO.
I'M SORRY
THAT YOU'RE SORRY.
WELL, I'M SORRY
THAT YOU'RE SORRY
THAT I'M SORRY.
TELL YOU WHAT --
I WON'T BE SORRY ANYMORE,
AND YOU DON'T BE SORRY,
EITHER, OKAY?
SORRY.
DAVIS, YOU SAVED THE DAY.
WE THOUGHT YOU WERE WONDERFUL.
RAYDRAMON, TOO.
[ MOANS ]
ARE YOU SICK?
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH HIM?
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I'M GETTING OUT OF HERE
BEFORE HE THROWS UP.
DAVIS,
YOU SAVED AGUMON,
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN LOSE
A SINGLE HAIR.
NOT YET.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY WERE ABLE TO DEFEAT
ONE OF MY NEW DARK SPIRALS.
I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE TO
MAKE THEM EVEN MORE POWERFUL.
IS IT OKAY
IF I DRIVE FOR A WHILE?
YOU SAID ONCE WE
TOOK OVER THE DIGIWORLD
THAT I COULD DRIVE.
HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE I TOLD YOU --
WHEN I'M THINKING,
DON'T TALK?
AND I AM
ALWAYS THINKING,
SO NEVER TALK!
WHY ARE EVIL GENIUSES
ALWAYS SURROUNDED BY FOOLS?
OKAY, WE MANAGED TO GET
AGUMON BACK SAFE AND SOUND,
BUT WE CAN'T RELAX
WITH KEN STILL OUT THERE.
TENTOMON, I NEED YOU TO BE A SPY
AND FIND OUT WHAT HE'S UP TO.
The name's Mon --
Tentomon.
WHOA! TWO DIGI-EGGS!
THAT'S COOL.
DAVIS, THANKS A LOT
FOR SAVING AGUMON.
YOU'RE A GOOD FRIEND.
WHO ME? A FRIEND?
THAT'S RIGHT. COME HERE.
YOU'RE OFFICIALLY PART
OF THE TEAM NOW.
TIME FOR A NOOGIE.
HEY, DID YOU SEE THAT?
I GOT A NOOGIE.
THAT MEANS I'M ONE
OF THE GUYS NOW.
IF YOU'RE ONE
OF THE GUYS NOW,
DOES THAT MEAN YOU USED TO BE
ONE OF THE GIRLS,
AND HOW COME YOU NEVER
TOLD ME ABOUT IT?
I WISH YOU HUMANS
WOULD MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
OKAY, THEN HOW IS THIS
FOR FRIENDSHIP?
HE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S GOT A LOT TO LEARN.
GREAT. TEACH ME.
YOU'LL LEARN SOON ENOUGH.
LET'S JUST TAKE IT
ONE STEP AT A TIME.
STARTING
WITH THE NOOGIES.
RIGHT.
OW, OW!
WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
EVER STOP
THE EVIL DIGIMON EMPEROR?
FIND OUT NEXT TIME ON
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."