Ken: BLACK WARGREYMON WAS READY
TO DESTROY
THE FINAL DESTINY STONES,
SO DAVIS HAD THE IDEA TO COMBINE
THE POWERS OF OUR D-3s.
THESE BRILLIANT BEAMS OF LIGHT
WERE RELEASED
AND AZULONMON WAS SET FREE.
BLACK WARGREYMON THOUGHT HE WAS
HIS ULTIMATE ENEMY AND ATTACKED,
BUT AZULONMON STOPPED HIM COLD
FOR A LITTLE REALITY CHECK.
IT TURNS OUT AZULONMON IS
ONE OF FOUR GUARDIANS
WHO WERE SEALED AWAY
BY THE DARK MASTERS.
HE TOLD BLACK WARGREYMON
THAT ALL CREATURES HAVE
A MEANING TO THEIR EXISTENCE,
SO BLACK WARGREYMON WENT OFF
TO FIND HIS.
WITH AZULONMON'S HELP,
HOPEFULLY, WE CAN REVERSE
ALL THE DAMAGE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
THAT I, UNFORTUNATELY,
HELPED INFLICT.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
V-LASER!
GRAND HORN!
TAIL HAMMER!
STAR SHOWER!
ROSETTA STONE!
SPIKING STRIKE!
Davis: YEAH, WE RULE!
Yolei: NYAH-NYAH!
TAKE THAT,
CONTROL SPIRES.
All: 2, 4, 6, 8,
WHO DO WE APPRECIATE?
US!
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D HAVE
FRIENDS LIKE THIS, WORMMON.
DON'T TELL ME,
TELL THEM.
BUT WHAT IF THEY DON'T WANT
TO COME TO MY PARTY?
OF COURSE THEY WILL.
HUH? KEN, GET OVER HERE
AND JOIN US.
HEY,
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
WELL, I --
AW, COME ON, KEN.
[ Thinking ] THIS
CHRISTMAS PARTY WAS A BAD IDEA.
I SHOULD
FORGET THE WHOLE THING,
BUT WHAT AM I GOING TO DO
WITH ALL THAT EGGNOG?
HEY, GUYS, KEN'S GOT
SOMETHING TO SHOW EVERYBODY.
[ Thinking ]
THANKS A LOT, DAVIS.
GREAT. NO PRESSURE.
COME ON, GUYS.
GATHER 'ROUND.
WHAT IS IT?
COOL.
REALLY?
WOW.
AHEM.
[ Nervously ]
I REQUEST THE HONOR
OF YOUR PRESENCE
AT A HOLIDAY CELEBRATION.
THAT IS, I --
SAY NO MORE.
YOU'RE HAVING
A CHRISTMAS PARTY. WE'RE IN.
COOL.
HEY, KEN,
CAN WE COME?
OF COURSE. MAYBE
YOU'LL EVEN CATCH GATOMON
UNDER THE MISTLETOE.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
[ Thinking ] IT LOOKS
LIKE CODY STILL HATES ME.
WELL, HERE GOES.
[ Thinking ] IT LOOKS
LIKE KEN STILL HATES ME.
WELL, HERE HE COMES.
HERE YOU GO, CODY.
YOU'RE INVITED, TOO.
REALLY? I'M GLAD
THAT I MADE YOUR LIST.
HA HA.
Man: ATTENTION,
HOLIDAY SHOPPERS.
GET INTO THE SPIRIT
OF THE SEASON
AND SPEND, SPEND, SPEND.
Woman: OH, YEAH, DON'T FORGET
ALL THE TEACHER GIFTS, TOO.
SORRY I'M SO LATE,
GUYS,
BUT THERE WAS
THIS REALLY CUTE GIRL
WHO WANTED MY AUTOGRAPH.
OH, THAT'S
A LAME EXCUSE.
ZIP IT.
ANYBODY EVER HEAR
OF REHEARSAL?
SORRY.
HUH?
Man: SORRY, MATT. I'M GOING
TO BE WORKING LATE TONIGHT.
YOU'LL HAVE TO MAKE
YOUR OWN DINNER, SPORT.
Matt: THAT'S OKAY, DAD.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
MY BAND'S GOT
A GIG TONIGHT ANYWAY.
BESIDES,
YOU'RE A LOUSY COOK.
VERY FUNNY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU SAID
WHEN YOU WOLFED DOWN
MY TUNA SURPRISE.
WELL, THE SURPRISE IS ON YOU,
DAD. I FED IT TO THE DOG.
SEE YOU.
DON'T WORK TOO LATE.
HUH? HMM.
I JUST LOVE THE HOLIDAYS,
MUMMYMON --
ALL THOSE SMILING FACES.
ALL THE BETTER WHEN WE GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO FROWN ABOUT.
THANKS FOR MEETING ME
AT THE MALL, MR. MOTOMIYA.
IT'S SO NICE OF YOU
TO RETURN T.K.'s HOMEWORK.
HE'S SO FORGETFUL.
AT LEAST YOUR SON
DOES HIS HOMEWORK.
I HAD SOME CHRISTMAS SHOPPING
TO DO ANYWAY.
I'M BUYING DAVIS A NOTEBOOK,
NOT THAT HE'LL EVER USE IT.
BY THE WAY, THANKS FOR ALWAYS
LETTING T.K. COME OVER.
IT REALLY HELPS ME OUT
SINCE I'M SO BUSY.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
T.K.'S A GREAT KID.
WELL, SEE YA.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
DON'T FORGET TO SAVE
THE NOTEBOOK RECEIPT.
HA. SO HE CAN EXCHANGE IT
FOR A SOCCER BALL? NO WAY.
AHH.
AH, MS. TAKAISHI.
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE
BUMPING INTO YOU HERE.
I HOPE YOU REMEMBER ME.
MR. OWAKAWA, IS IT?
YES.
RIGHT. YOU INVESTIGATED
THE HEIGHTENED VIEW
TERRORIST INCIDENT
EIGHT YEARS AGO.
IT'S SO NICE
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
YES, IT IS.
BY THE WAY, REMEMBER
THE ODAIBA FOG INCIDENT?
WELL, I'M AFRAID
THIS CURRENT MONSTER PROBLEM
IS RELATED.
IN FACT, IT'S ONLY
JUST THE BEGINNING.
HUH? WELL,
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT --
"ONLY JUST THE BEGINNING"?
YOU'LL FIND OUT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL
OF WHO YOU LET YOUR SONS
PLAY WITH.
MY SONS?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT T.K. AND MATT?
ACTUALLY, I KNOW
EVERYTHING, MY DEAR.
ENJOY THE HOLIDAYS.
IT'S THE MOST WONDERFUL TIME
OF THE YEAR.
HUH? HE'S GONE.
[ Thinking ] WHAT HAVE THE BOYS
GOT THEMSELVES MIXED UP IN NOW?
I THOUGHT ALL THAT DIGITAL WORLD
STUFF WAS OVER WITH.
NOW THE DANGER STARTS
ALL OVER AGAIN.
DAVIS, YOO-HOO.
IT'S ME -- AGUMON.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
WHAT'S CHRISTMAS?
IT'S MEANS YOU'RE GOING
TO BE THE BEST PRESENT
THE ORIGINAL DIGIDESTINED
EVER GOT.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
MIMI'S IN AMERICA.
DON'T WORRY, PALMON.
WE WOULDN'T LET EVERYBODY
JOIN UP WITH THEIR PARTNERS
AND LEAVE YOU OUT.
OH, I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE MIMI.
THIS WILL BE A SNAP.
WE'LL OPEN UP A PORTAL
FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD
THAT WILL DROP PALMON OFF
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF DOWNTOWN U.S. OF A.
SAY HI TO MIMI FOR ME,
AND WHEN YOU COME BACK,
SEE IF SHE'LL LET ME BORROW
THAT PINK BLOUSE I LOVE SO MUCH.
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
DON'T WORRY.
WAIT! FIRST, I --
WHAT --
[ MUFFLED SPEECH ]
MIMI'S GOING TO BE
SO SURPRISED
WHEN SHE WAKES UP.
HA HA HA.
MRS. ICHIJOUJI,
YOU CAN GO HOME NOW.
QUITTING TIME.
OH, ALREADY? I FEEL
LIKE I JUST STARTED.
GO HOME
TO THAT SON OF YOURS.
HE SURE HAS CHANGED
RECENTLY.
I CALLED AND WE HAD
THE MOST LOVELY CONVERSATION.
HE NEVER WOULD'VE
BOTHERED HIMSELF
WITH SUCH TRIVIALITIES
AS ANSWERING THE PHONE BEFORE.
WHAT BROUGHT ON
THE PLEASANT CHANGE?
OH, I GUESS IT'S JUST
THE HOLIDAY SPIRIT.
MERRY CHRISTMAS. HA HA.
Agumon:
LET ME OUT OF HERE, DAVIS.
I KNOW I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
A PRESENT,
BUT DID YOU HAVE TO
GIFT-WRAP ME?
SHH. YOU'LL RUIN
THE SURPRISE, AGUMON.
WAIT TILL I GIVE YOU
THE SIGNAL.
NOW!
SURPRISE!
WELL, AGUMON.
NO WAY!
GABUMON!
GOOD TO SEE YOU,
IZZY.
GOMAMON,
DON'T SQUEEZE SO HARD.
I'LL GET A CRAMP.
I THINK THEY LIKE
THEIR PRESENTS.
JUST CALL ME
DAVIS CLAUS.
JUST WHAT I WANTED.
HOW'D YOU KNOW?
A LITTLE BIRDRAMON
TOLD US.
THIS IS NICE.
CHRISTMAS IS A TIME
FOR FAMILIES TO GET TOGETHER.
WOW, THIS IS SO EXCITING.
PEOPLE ARE ALREADY LINING UP
FOR MATT'S CONCERT.
DON'T WORRY, SORA,
WE'LL BE SURE
TO GET GOOD SEATS.
ESPECIALLY ONCE YOU GIVE HIM
THESE HOMEMADE COOKIES.
I HOPE.
SORA, WAIT UP.
OH, TAI. UH...
Agumon:
SOMETHING SMELLS GOOD.
MATT'S BUSY
GETTING READY,
BUT I'LL TAKE THOSE
TO HIM. MMM.
I BET YOU WILL. NO WAY.
YOU'LL EAT THE WHOLE THING
YOURSELF.
WHY, I RESENT THAT.
I'M ON A DIET.
Tai: SO, UM, SORA,
ARE YOU GOING
TO THE CONCERT
WITH ANYBODY?
I MEAN, NOT THAT
IT MATTERS TO ME.
UH, JUST WONDERING.
NO, I WANT TO BE
AVAILABLE
IN CASE MATT IS FREE
AFTERWARDS.
[ GIGGLES ]
OH, I SEE. MATT, HUH?
UM, UH...
IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT
MAD AT ME, TAI?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
NOW GET IN THERE
AND SAY HI TO MATT FOR ME.
THANKS, TAI.
THE LEAST YOU CAN DO IS
LEAVE US THE COOKIES.
[ Giggles ]
TELL YOU WHAT --
I'LL MAKE SOME SPECIAL ONES
FOR YOU.
I'LL BE WAITING.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW WHAT, TAI?
WHAT?
YOU'VE REALLY GROWN UP.
June:
LOOK OUT! INCOMING!
Both: HUH? WHOA!
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
JUNE.
SORRY. I'M IN A HURRY
TO SEE MATT.
ALL THE GIRLS THINK
HE'S THE CUTEST.
Ken: AND THIS IS MY ROOM.
NOTHING FANCY.
OOH.
THIS IS A GOOD PICTURE
OF YOU, KEN.
UM, IT'S NOT ME.
IT'S MY OLDER BROTHER SAM.
OH, I'M SORRY.
HMM.
Matt: ARE YOU READY TO ROCK?
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING ]
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDER ]
♪ YOU GOT A BOY,
YOU GOT A GIRL ♪
♪ SITTING UNDERNEATH A TREE ♪
♪ THEY SIT THERE EVERY DAY ♪
♪ AND EVEN THOUGH YOU MAY THINK
THIS IS THE WAY ♪
MATT IS
A REALLY GOOD SINGER,
THOUGH I MAY BE BIASED.
I LOVE YOU, MATT!
I'M YOUR NUMBER ONE FAN!
YAY!
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING ]
Arachnemon: I LOVE
A GOOD CONCERT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
MUMMYMON, WE'RE GOING
TO BRING A NEW MEANING
TO THE PHRASE
"MONSTERS OF ROCK." HA HA!
♪ I'LL TURN BACK THE ROAD,
MAKE YOU SEE WHAT'S AHEAD ♪
♪ AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE
I'VE BEEN HERE ALL ALONG ♪
♪ JUST TURN AROUND ♪
HUH?
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
I HOPE THIS IS
PART OF THE SHOW.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WITH ROCK CONCERTS.
HUH?
THERE'S A BUNCH
OF STATIC COMING THROUGH.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WE'RE ON LIVE!
[ GROWLS ]
WHAT'S THAT?
GRRAAH!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
WHAT ARE THEY
DOING HERE?
MAYBE THEY'RE
JUST MUSIC LOVERS.
GRRAAH!
WHAT A CONCERT!
THESE CRAZY KIDS!
YEAH, WOODSTOCK --
NOW THAT WAS A CONCERT.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
AGUMON, DIGIVOLVE!
RIGHT.
[ Grunts ] I CAN'T, TAI.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DID YOU FORGET HOW?
NEVER MIND!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
[ GROWLING ]
Tai: THERE'S ANOTHER ONE!
[ SCREAMING ]
YEAH, I HAVE ONE --
RUN!
HUH? A CONTROL SPIRE?
GOT ANY 3's?
NO, NO, NO, NO!
JUST SAY "GO FISH."
YOU'LL GET
THE HANG OF IT, YOLEI.
AAH! I CAN'T
EVEN LEARN GO FISH.
[ ALL LAUGH ]
[ LAUGHING ]
HUH? DID YOU SEE
WHAT I SAW?
KEN JUST LAUGHED.
WHAT A GREAT SMILE.
KEN, YOU SHOULD TRY
TO LAUGH MORE OFTEN.
THANKS A LOT.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ Thinking ] IT'S SO NICE
TO HAVE A HOUSE FULL
OF LAUGHING CHILDREN AGAIN.
OH, DEAR,
I'M GETTING ALL MISTY.
OH, I PROMISED MYSELF
I WOULDN'T CRY.
QUICK, THINK SAD THOUGHTS.
OH, THE PHONE. COME NOW,
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
HI.
ICHIJOUJI RESIDENCE.
MY DEAL. WHAT DO YOU GUYS
WANT TO PLAY?
HOW ABOUT STRIP POKER?
KEN, SOME BOY NAMED TAI'S
ON THE PHONE
FOR YOUR FRIEND KARI.
SOMETHING
MUST BE WRONG.
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
GRRAAH!
HEY!
YOU RUINED MY CONCERT!
MATT, GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE FOCUSED.
THERE THEY ARE.
COME ON, DAVIS.
CAN'T WE MOVE ANY FASTER?
DON'T BE
A BACK SEAT DRIVER, KEN.
[ Thinking ]
A CONTROL SPIRE?
NO WONDER TAI NEEDS US.
WELL, IF IT'S HELP HE NEEDS,
IT'S HELP HE'LL GET.
THUNDER BLAST!
ROCK CRACKING!
Davis: GOING DOWN?
IT'S TIME FOR US
TO CLEAN UP THIS MESS.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPION.
WORMMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
STINGMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
LET'S DO IT
OLD SCHOOL STYLE.
MM.
AGUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GREYMON!
EVERYONE...
DIGIVOLVE...
RIGHT NOW!
HURRY!
BIYOMON...
GABUMON...
GOMAMON...
TENTOMON...
All: DIGIVOLVE TO...
BIRDRAMON!
GARURUMON!
IKKAKUMON!
KABUTERIMON!
NOVA BLAST!
MATT! T.K.!
QUICK, TURN THE CAMERAS ON.
THIS IS GREAT STUFF.
THIS WILL BE THE HIGHEST-RATED
SHOW WE'VE EVER HAD.
WE'LL EVEN GET
A RAISE.
IF ANYONE'S LEFT
TO GIVE IT.
METEOR WING!
HA! MISSED ME.
IS IT JUST ME,
OR ISN'T THIS EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED FOUR YEARS AGO?
SURROUND HIM,
KABUTERIMON!
DIDN'T WE MEET
IN METAL SHOP?
Yolei: I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
THEY CAN KEEP THIS UP.
I KNEW DAVIS LIKED ACTION,
BUT THIS?
HEARTS ATTACK!
THEY'RE ALL OVER THE PLACE!
YEAH, THEY'VE GOT US
OUTNUMBERED.
WAIT,
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
EVERYONE, GET ALL
THE EVIL DIGIMON
TOGETHER
IN ONE PLACE.
WE'RE GOING TO SEND THEM
BACK TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
HALSEMON!
AT YOUR SERVICE.
TEMPEST WING!
READY, PARTNER?
LET'S TIE ONE ON.
Both: GOLDEN NOOSE!
IS YOUR LAPTOP READY,
IZZY?
READY AND ABLE.
THEN WHAT ARE
WE WAITING FOR?
DIGIPORT OPEN...
NOW!
WELL, THAT WASN'T
SO HARD.
EASY AS PIE.
Kari: OH, BOY.
WE SHOULD MAKE IT A RULE
THAT TAI AND DAVIS
AREN'T ALLOWED
TO BE TOGETHER
IN THE SAME ROOM.
FORGET ABOUT THEM,
KARI.
IT'S THE DIGIMON
THAT WORRY ME.
HOW'D THEY GET HERE
TO OUR WORLD
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
NOT TO MENTION
THAT CONTROL SPIRE.
WHAT IF IT'S
A BRAND-NEW ENEMY?
SEE YOU AROUND --
NOT.
LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
I'M PRETTY SURE
I KNOW WHO'S BEHIND ALL THIS.
IT'S GOT TO BE
ARACHNEMON.
YOU THINK SO?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
SHE'S INVOLVED?
BECAUSE SHE'S ABLE
TO MOVE FREELY
BETWEEN THE TWO WORLDS.
Tai: BIRDRAMON! NEFERTIMON!
MORE LEFT TO GO!
WHO TURNED OUT
THE LIGHTS?
PUSH 'EM BACK,
PUSH 'EM BACK, WAY BACK.
JUST TWO ULTIMATES LEFT.
DAVIS, KEN, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO DO THE HONORS?
Both: MM-HMM.
NEW PLAN, GUYS!
WE HAVE TO FIGHT ULTIMATES
WITH ULTIMATES.
GO BACK
TO YOUR ROOKIE STAGES
AND GET READY
TO DNA DIGIVOLVE!
VEEMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
X-VEEMON!
HAWKMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
AQUILAMON!
ARMADILLOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANKYLOMON!
PATAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
NOW LET'S SEE WHAT ALL THIS
DNA FUSS IS ABOUT.
SHOW HIM, GUYS!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
X-VEEMON!
STINGMON!
Both: DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
PAILDRAMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
AQUILAMON!
GATOMON!
Both: DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
SILPHYMON!
ANKYLOMON!
ANGEMON!
Both: DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
SHAKKOUMON!
STING STRIKE!
OUTSIDE ATTACK!
STATIC FORCE!
HEARTS ATTACK!
HAKINA BOMB!
♪ LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I AIN'T SEEN
THE LAST OF ME AND YOU ♪
BEDTIME.
♪ LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
♪ TOGETHER ♪
DON'T FORGET
YOUR TEDDY BEAR.
AND TO ALL,
A GOOD NIGHT.
YEAH! WE DID IT.
ALL THE DIGIDESTINED TOGETHER --
THE ULTIMATE TEAMWORK.
GUYS, IF ARACHNEMON
AND HER DIGIMON
CAN MOVE
BETWEEN WORLDS,
THEN WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
WHAT'LL WE DO?
WE'LL HAVE TO FIGHT
ALL OVER AGAIN.
OH, NO.
HUH?
RELAX. WE'LL GET HER.
HMM.
YEAH!
Ken: THANKS FOR WALKING ME
TO THE TRAIN, EVERYONE.
I GUESS MY PARTY
IS OVER, HUH?
IT WAS SHORT,
BUT IT WAS FUN.
WE HAD A GREAT TIME,
KEN.
ME, TOO. THANKS.
AND WE'RE ALL GOING
TO COME OVER NEXT YEAR.
MERRY CHRISTMAS
AND A HAPPY NEW YEAR.
YOU, TOO.
OH, NO.
I FORGOT TO KISS KARI
UNDER THE MISTLETOE.
HE NEVER QUITS.
DAVIS,
TAKE IT FROM ME --
YOU'LL NEVER LEARN
ABOUT WOMEN.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
HA!
AAH!
AGUMON, YOU ARE
THE BEST PRESENT EVER.
CAN YOU STAY THROUGH
TILL NEW YEAR'S?
I THOUGHT
YOU'D NEVER ASK ME.
BE CAREFUL, GUYS.
YOU JUST ATE.
I DON'T WANT YOU
LOSING YOUR CHRISTMAS DINNER
ON MY BED.
[ YAWNS ]
TELL ME A CHRISTMAS
BEDTIME STORY,
WOULD YOU, TAI?
I KNOW ONE.
'TWAS A DIGIMON CHRISTMAS,
AND EVERYONE WAS BUSY,
ESPECIALLY THE LIKES
OF TENTOMON AND IZZY.
JOE PLAYED WITH GOMAMON,
MATT AND GABUMON ATE,
PALMON SAW MIMI.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
CODY AND UPAMON
SHARED A LITTLE SUSHI
WHILE PARURUMON SAT
ON YOLEI'S TUSHIE.
TOKOMON WENT CAROLING,
KEN'S THANKFUL FOR FRIENDS,
WHILE IN DAVIS' DREAMS,
THE FUN NEVER ENDS.
GOOD NIGHT, NOW.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
June: DAVIS, WAKE UP!
Man: WE NOW BRING YOU
THIS SPECIAL REPORT.
WHY? WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE'VE RECEIVED
MANY EYEWITNESS REPORTS
ON YESTERDAY'S
MONSTER ATTACK DOWNTOWN,
INCLUDING SIGHTINGS
OF MYSTERIOUS BLACK OBELISKS.
INTERNATIONAL REPORTS
NOW CONFIRM
THESE TOWERS ARE APPEARING
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
[ BOTH GASP ]
IT'S JUST LIKE THE ONE
AT MATT'S CONCERT.
MORE CONTROL SPIRES.
AAH!
WHAT'S THE MATTER, IZZY?
DID YOUR COMPUTER
FREEZE AGAIN?
IT'S EVEN WORSE.
LOOK AT THIS.
DIGIPORTS ARE OPENING
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
OH, NO!
AND THERE'S NOTHING
WE CAN DO TO STOP IT.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
IT COULD BE
SANTA'S NEW WAY
OF DELIVERING TOYS, HMM?
NOW WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO DO?
WHO IS MYSTERIOUSLY OPENING
ALL THE DIGIPORTS
AROUND THE WORLD?
FIND OUT NEXT TIME
ON "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."