WE HAD A COOL REUNION
TO CELEBRATE THE ANNIVERSARY
OF OUR FIRST TRIP
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
US OLDER DIGIDESTINED
FILLED IN THE NEW ONES
ABOUT THE STORIES
FROM THE EARLY DAYS.
WE DIDN'T KNOW
THERE WAS A STRANGE DARK SHADOW
THAT HAD STARTED APPEARING
ALL OVER THE TV STATION.
IT WAS OUR OLD FRIEND
WIZARDMON.
HE'D COME TO WARN US
THAT THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
ISN'T THE ONLY EVIL
TO WATCH OUT FOR.
THERE'S SOMETHING
EVEN MORE POWERFUL OUT THERE,
AND THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN DEFEAT IT IS
WITH THE GOLDEN RADIANCE.
I WONDER WHAT HE MEANS.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Davis: HAVE TO FIND
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
I HOPE THE OTHERS
ARE HAVING LUCK.
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
I WONDER
HOW CODY'S DOING.
AAH!
YOU OKAY, CODY?
OH, OH, YES,
THANKS TO YOU.
YOU CAN MAKE IT.
WE'RE ALMOST AT THE TOP.
YOU TWO, GET UP HERE.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE,
TENTOMON.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I TOLD YOU.
I'M SEEING THINGS,
I THINK.
DIG THIS.
WOW. LOOK AT ALL THOSE.
THERE'S HUNDREDS
OF CONTROL SPIRES.
AND HUNDREDS
OF EVIL DIGIMON SLAVES, TOO.
THOSE POOR DIGIMON.
IT SEEMS TO ME
THE DARK TYRANNOMON
ARE COMING OUT
OF THAT STRANGE DOME.
I'LL BET YOU THAT'S WHERE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
HEADQUARTERS ARE.
UH-OH.
WE BETTER TAKE COVER.
I HOPE WE DON'T NEED
YOUR HELP.
NO WAY YOU CAN DIGIVOLVE
WITH ALL THESE CONTROL SPIRES.
MAYBE THEY HAVEN'T
SPOTTED US YET.
I KNEW I SHOULD HAVE
BROUGHT MY FLY SWATTER.
GET HIM, DIGMON.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
ARMADILLOMON
ARMADIGIVOLVE TO...
DIGMON,
THE DRILL OF POWER.
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
MAY I HAVE THIS DANCE?
MY D-3 IS GOING WILD. WHOA!
GOING SOMEWHERE?
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR!
SO NICE OF YOU TO DROP IN
ON MY HEADQUARTERS.
IT SAVES ME THE TIME
OF HUNTING YOU DOWN.
I'VE GOT TO TRY
THE DIGIVOLVE.
GO.
TENTOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
OH, FORGET IT.
I CAN'T DIGIVOLVE.
HA HA HA!
HOW MANY TIMES DO I
HAVE TO TELL YOU PEOPLE
YOU'RE SITTING IN
THE NO-DIGIVOLVING SECTION?
THANKS, DIGMON.
DO I KNOW HOW
TO DIG A HOLE OR WHAT?
OKAY, WE'RE IN THE CLEAR.
THERE ARE NO
CONTROL SPIRES HERE.
TENTOMON!
I'LL GIVE IT ANOTHER SHOT.
TENTOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
KABUTERIMON.
SO THAT'S KABUTERIMON.
I THINK I'LL ADD HIM
TO MY COLLECTION.
HA HA HA!
THAT'S EVERYONE.
IS MY MOM HERE?
NO, WE WERE LUCKY.
WE MADE IT BACK
BEFORE SHE GOT HOME.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
WHAT DID YOU FIND
IN YOUR AREA?
THE PLACE WAS COVERED
WITH CONTROL SPIRES.
I KNEW IT.
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
A CONTROL SPIRE CONVENTION.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
THERE WERE HUNDREDS.
WE FOUND SOMETHING ELSE,
TOO --
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S BASE.
HIS BASE?
YEAH.
I'll keep my eyes
on things here
and report back
if there's trouble.
RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT,
EVERYBODY SHOULD
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
All: HUH?
FIRST, LOOK AT THE AREA
DAVIS EXPLORED.
NEXT IS THE AREA
THAT T.K.'s GROUP WAS IN.
FINALLY,
HERE'S WHERE MY GROUP WAS.
IF WE CONNECT THEM
TOGETHER...
IT'S A CIRCUS CLOWN.
I LOVE THIS GAME.
NO, DAVIS, IT'S A PATH.
HE'S TAKING OVER
ALL THE AREAS.
THERE WILL BE NOTHING LEFT
OF OUR WORLD.
NOT TO MENTION
OUR FRIENDS.
THAT'S IT. NOW I'M REALLY
STARTING TO GET UPSET.
IF WE COULD ONLY
DESTROY THAT BASE.
THAT'S IT.
IF WE DESTROY
THE EMPEROR'S HEADQUARTERS,
THEN THE CONTROL SPIRES
WILL BE USELESS.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
SO WHY ARE WE SITTING AROUND
LIKE A BUNCH OF YAHOOS?
I SAY WE GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
FIND HIS BASE, AND RIP IT UP
LIKE A BAD CHECK.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO,
WALK UP THERE AND SAY,
"EXCUSE ME, DO YOU MIND IF
WE TEAR DOWN THIS BUILDING?"
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
I SUPPOSE WE HAVE TO COME UP
WITH SOME SORT OF PLAN.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
A LOT OF THINKING.
I ALSO THINK
IT'S GOING TO TAKE LONGER
THAN ONE DAY TO ACCOMPLISH.
I SUPPOSE IF WE ALL HAD TO
BE BACK BY A CERTAIN TIME,
WE WOULDN'T CONCENTRATE
ON DESTROYING THE BASE.
THEN WE ALL HAVE TO
AGREE ON ONE THING --
WE DON'T RETURN
UNTIL THE BASE IS DESTROYED.
YOU MEAN --
IF I'M NOT THERE
FOR MY MOM'S TUNA CASSEROLE,
SHE'LL KNOW
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I HAVEN'T MISSED ONE
IN TWO YEARS.
MAKE UP SOME EXCUSE
TO TELL HER.
YOU GOT PICKED FOR A SECRET
MISSION TO MARS.
IF YOU TOLD YOUR PARENTS THAT,
THEY'D BELIEVE YOU?
THEY DON'T BELIEVE
ANYTHING I SAY.
WITH ALL THESE CONTROL SPIRES
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
THERE'S NO WAY OUR DIGIMON
WILL BE ABLE TO DIGIVOLVE.
THAT MEANS US OLDER KIDS
WOULD BE USELESS IF WE GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
WITH YOU GUYS.
THERE ARE OTHER WAYS WE CAN HELP
WITHOUT GOING WITH THEM.
WHILE YOU GUYS GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
THE REST OF US WILL GO
ON A CAMPING TRIP.
HOW DOES IT HELP
IF WE'RE FIGHTING WHILE
YOU'RE ROASTING MARSHMALLOWS?
WE'LL TELL OUR PARENTS
WE'RE GOING CAMPING,
BUT IF THEY CALL
THE CAMPGROUNDS
AND NO ONE'S THERE,
WE'LL GET IN TROUBLE,
SO THE OLDER KIDS
WILL GO CAMPING FOR REAL.
GREAT IDEA, TAI --
PLUS WE GET TO GO CAMPING.
SOMEONE'S GOT TO DO IT.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ Gulps ] COME IN.
OH, YOU'RE HOME.
HELLO.
HI THERE, MOM.
All: HELLO, MRS. IZUMI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING INSIDE
ON SUCH A NICE DAY?
All: WELL...
Izzy: WE WERE DISCUSSING
GOING ON A CAMPING TRIP
FOR OUR NEXT VACATION.
THAT SOUNDS FUN, BUT YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED A CHAPERON.
WHO'S THE ADULT
THAT'S GOING WITH YOU?
UH...
MY DAD WILL GO WITH US.
HE LOVES TRAVELING THE WORLD.
Are you sure?
No, but it sounded good.
WHAT? YOU WANT ME
TO GO CAMPING WITH YOU?
I ALREADY PROMISED
THE OTHERS YOU WOULD DO IT.
JUST THINK OF IT --
BEING OUT IN THE WILDERNESS
AMONG ALL THE SNAKES
AND THE WOLVES. IT'LL BE FUN.
[ GROANS ]
HEY, DAD?
TELL US AGAIN ABOUT THE TIME
YOU WERE CHASED BY A BEAR.
DON'T YOU KIDS
HAVE HOMEWORK?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE PACKING
FOR A CAMPING TRIP.
IT'S YOUR IMAGINATION.
ARE T.K.
AND THE OTHERS GOING?
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
SO, THEN, IS MATT
GOING CAMPING, TOO?
MATT MOVED
TO ANOTHER COUNTRY.
WELL, IF YOU'RE GOING
AND EVERYONE ELSE IS GOING
AND MATT'S GOING,
CAN I GO, TOO?
SURE YOU CAN GO.
GO AWAY.
POLICE STILL HAVE NO CLUE
AS TO THE WHEREABOUTS
OF BOY GENIUS KEN ICHIJOUJI,
WHO DISAPPEARED SOME TIME AGO.
IF ANYONE
HAS SEEN MY SON,
PLEASE CONTACT THE POLICE
RIGHT AWAY.
THAT KID'S STILL LOST?
I HOPE HE'S NOT ALONE
SOMEWHERE, COLD AND HUNGRY.
OH, HE'S HELPLESS
WITHOUT ME.
BOY, IF THEY ONLY KNEW.
[ GROANS ]
T.K.'s voice: I ALSO THINK
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
LONGER THAN ONE DAY
TO ACCOMPLISH.
Kari's voice: RIGHT.
THEN WE ALL HAVE TO
AGREE ON ONE THING --
WE DON'T RETURN UNTIL
THE BASE IS DESTROYED.
ALL RIGHT, EVEN THOUGH
I'M GOING TO BE GONE A LONG TIME
AND I'LL MISS MY SOAP OPERAS,
I AM TOTALLY UP FOR THIS!
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE UP AT ALL.
WE WENT TO BED HOURS AGO.
SOME OF US ARE TRYING
TO SLEEP. GOOD NIGHT.
YEAH, GOOD NIGHT.
[ Thinking ] GO, YOLEI,
GO, YOLEI, GO.
GO, YOLEI, GO, YOLEI, GO.
DIGIMON EMPEROR,
PREPARE TO GO DOWN!
WE'RE GOING TO TEACH
THAT EVIL GENIUS
A LESSON
HE'LL NEVER FORGET!
SHE'S EXCITED.
SHE'S BEEN LIKE THIS
ALL NIGHT.
YAAH! HYAH!
HYAH!
HEY, YOLEI, SAVE SOME
FOR THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
LEFT, RIGHT,
LEFT, RIGHT, AND HALT.
SIR, YES, SIR.
YOU GOT A LOT TO LEARN
ABOUT WOMEN, T.K.
ALL RIGHT! TIME TO GO!
LET THE BATTLE BEGIN!
DIGIPORT OPEN! YEE-HA!
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
YOU RUGGED CAMPING MEN
ALL SET TO GO?
YEP. THANKS FOR TAKING US.
WELL, I GUESS
WE SHOULD GET GOING.
RIGHT.
HI THERE, MATT.
I'M READY.
All: HUH?
ISN'T THAT DAVIS' SISTER?
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
WELL, SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO
TO GET RID OF HER, OKAY?
RIGHT.
HEY, JUNE,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THOUGHT
THIS CAMPING TRIP
WOULD BE A PERFECT
ROMANTIC GETAWAY FOR US.
Izzy: LUCKY MATT.
GIRLS MUST CHASE HIM
ALL DAY.
I KNOW EXACTLY
HOW HE FEELS.
BY THE WAY, WHERE'S DAVIS
AND THE OTHERS?
OH, THOSE GUYS --
THEY WENT AHEAD OF US
IN ANOTHER CAR.
A FRIEND OF MY DAD'S
HAS A REALLY BIG MINIVAN.
HMM. WHERE DO I SIT?
UH, FIRST I HAVE
A PRESENT TO GIVE YOU.
HUH? ME?
YEAH, BUT IT'S IN THE CAR,
AND I DIDN'T WRAP IT,
SO CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND COUNT TO 10
AND I'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH YOUR PRESENT, OKAY?
[ Giggles ] OKAY, MATT.
1...
Matt: OKAY, DAD,
STEP ON IT.
YOU WANT
TO LEAVE HER HERE?
YEP.
YOU HAVE A LOT TO LEARN
ABOUT WOMEN, MATT.
HMM, WHERE DID I
HEAR THAT BEFORE?
9, 10.
HUH?
MATT!
WHERE'S MY PRESENT?
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
BASE IS UP HERE.
FOLLOW ME.
YOLEI, THIS ISN'T
A TRACK MEET.
HUH?
I HATE TO BE
A FLY IN YOUR SOUP,
BUT THE EMPEROR'S BASE
IS GONE.
HUH?
IT CAN'T BE.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
HIS BASE WAS RIGHT HERE.
MAYBE IT WAS
A MOBILE HOME.
SINCE HE WAS LEAVING,
HE COULD HAVE DONE
THE POLITE THING
AND TAKEN THOSE CONTROL
SPIRES WITH HIM.
HAS ANYONE SEEN YOLEI?
LOOK DOWN THERE.
YOLEI, CAN'T WE TAKE
THE SCENIC ROUTE?
[ ALL GASP ]
ARE YOU SURE YOU SAW IT?
MAYBE IT WAS A GARAGE.
YOU MEAN A MIRAGE?
NO, I MEANT A PLACE WHERE
THE EMPEROR KEEPS HIS CAR.
HOW CAN A WHOLE BUILDING
DISAPPEAR INTO THIN AIR?
MAYBE KEN'S FRIENDS
WITH A REALLY GOOD MAGICIAN.
WHAT DO WE DO?
WE KEEP ON LOOKING.
WE PROMISED NOT TO LEAVE
UNTIL THE BASE IS DESTROYED.
LEAVE IT TO ME.
I'LL FIND HIS HEADQUARTERS.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS FOLLOW
THE BUILDING TRACKS.
Yolei: UP HERE!
All: HUH?
YOLEI SEEMS
TO BE LOSING IT.
[ PANTING ]
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED --
THE ENTIRE BUILDING JUST
FLEW RIGHT UP INTO THE SKY.
RIDICULOUS.
IF THAT HAPPENED,
SOMEONE
WOULD HAVE SEEN IT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT WAS YOU!
YOU WERE GUARDING THIS AREA
THE ENTIRE TIME WE WERE GONE.
TELL US WHAT YOU SAW
OR ELSE.
STOP YELLING AT TENTOMON,
YOLEI. HE TRIED.
WELL, HE SHOULD HAVE
TRIED HARDER!
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY,
TENTOMON.
YOLEI DOESN'T MEAN
ANY OF THIS.
SHE'S BEEN UNDER
STRAIN LATELY.
MUST SHE YELL AT ME?
CAN'T SHE TAKE A YOGA CLASS?
WHAT'S SHE DOING NOW?
I'M NOT GOING TO ASK HER
AS LONG AS SHE HAS
THAT HAMMER.
I'M OFF TO SCOUT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
UNDERGROUND EMPIRE.
I'LL REPORT BACK SOON.
YOLEI, WAIT FOR ME!
[ ALL GROAN ]
YOLEI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU LOSING YOUR MIND?
WHAT HAS GOTTEN
INTO YOU LATELY?
LEAVE ME ALONE, HAWKMON.
I'M A HIGHLY
MOTIVATED WOMAN,
AND I CAN ACHIEVE ANY GOAL
I SET MY SIGHTS ON.
[ ROARS ]
HUH?
OH, NO, IT'S THE DREADED
DOKUGUMON.
HE'S AN INSECT-TYPE DIGIMON
WHOSE SPECIAL ATTACK
IS POISON THREAD.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
CAUGHT UP IN HIS WEB.
AAH!
POISON THREAD!
YOLEI!
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
HAWKMON!
HAWKMON, YOLEI,
GET OUT OF THERE!
[ ROARS ]
DAVIS!
RIGHT!
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE.
HAWKMON, SPEAK TO ME.
PULL, EVERYONE! PULL!
HAWKMON, HANG ON.
FIRE ROCKET!
WE GOT YOU, YOLEI.
HAWKMON!
HAWKMON! HAWKMON!
Flamedramon: YOU'RE BUSTED.
HMM...
HOW'S HAWKMON DOING?
I THINK HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WE WRAPPED HIM UP
IN BANDAGES.
WE HAVE TO KEEP HIM SAFE
UNTIL HE HEALS.
HE SURE WAS BRAVE
SAVING YOLEI LIKE THAT.
HAWKMON!
[ CRYING ]
YOLEI?
HUH?
I'LL STAY HERE AND TAKE CARE
OF HAWKMON, OKAY?
YOU GUYS, GO OUT AND FIND
THE EMPEROR'S HEADQUARTERS.
BUT --
I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE TROUBLE
FOR ANYONE ELSE.
PLEASE, JUST GO.
ALL RIGHT, THEN,
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
HUH?
HE'S RIGHT. LET'S GO.
RIGHT.
I'LL STAY HERE.
YOU WILL?
MORE OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
SLAVES MIGHT ATTACK,
SO WE'D BETTER HAVE GATOMON
AROUND AS A BODYGUARD.
GOOD POINT.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
WE CAN ALWAYS E-MAIL EACH OTHER
AND YOU'LL ALWAYS KNOW
WHERE WE ARE THROUGH THE D-3s.
IF WE HAVEN'T FOUND THE BASE
BY NIGHTFALL,
WE'LL COME BACK HERE, OKAY?
OKAY.
BE CAREFUL.
YEAH, YOU, TOO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT US.
WE'VE GOT DAVIS.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
GO WRONG?
HA HA HA!
HEY, YOLEI?
WHAT?
I KNOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT
AND WIN THIS BATTLE
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU'RE GOING ABOUT IT
THE WRONG WAY.
I TRIED THE SAME THING
ONE TIME,
BUT I WAS WRONG, TOO.
WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
AS A TEAM, RIGHT, KARI?
MM-HMM. NOW YOU GET IT.
WELL, I'M GLAD WE GOT
THAT STRAIGHTENED OUT.
NOW I'M GOING TO SEE
IF I CAN FIND SOME HERBS
TO HELP HAWKMON.
THERE'S A LOT OF CONTROL SPIRES
AROUND HERE.
I'M GETTING TIRED
OF ALL THIS CONSTRUCTION
IN MY BEAUTIFUL FOREST.
DON'T WORRY.
WHEN WE'RE THROUGH HERE,
THIS PLACE WILL BE
GOOD AS NEW.
HUH?
HEY, CODY, WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M NOT SURE.
I SAW SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS,
BUT IT CAME
FROM OVER THERE --
SOME KIND OF SHADOW.
HEY, CODY,
THIS ISN'T A TOUR.
COME ON.
OH, SORRY. I'M COMING.
NEXT.
AHA.
I TOLD YOU TO BE FINISHED
AN HOUR AGO.
SORRY, MASTER. I HAD
TO FINISH THE DISHES.
HEADS -- I WIN.
WE LOSE.
[ GROANS ]
WHERE AM I?
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
JUST RELAX.
HAWKMON, WHAT CAN I DO
TO APOLOGIZE?
JUST GET OFF MY TAIL.
OH.
I FOUND CATNIP.
IT CURES IT ALL.
OKAY, BUT LET'S
GIVE THEM A MINUTE.
HUH?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS MY CHANCE
TO PROVE TO MYSELF
THAT I WAS AS STRONG
AS EVERYONE ELSE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT TAKING
MATTERS INTO MY OWN HANDS
COULD WIND UP HURTING SOMEONE,
ESPECIALLY YOU.
I WAS TOO STUBBORN.
HA HA HA!
HAWKMON, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU TODAY IS ALL MY FAULT.
WHEN MY MIND GETS SET
ON SOMETHING,
I JUST CAN'T STOP
UNTIL I'M FINISHED.
I'LL UNDERSTAND IF YOU
WANT TO FIND SOMEONE ELSE
TO BE YOUR PARTNER
FROM NOW ON.
YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT, YOLEI.
THOSE QUALITIES
YOU DESCRIBED
ARE WHAT MAKES YOU
WHO YOU ARE.
HUH?
[ GROANS ]
YOLEI, I LIKE YOU
EXACTLY THE WAY YOU ARE.
[ SIGHS ]
THANK YOU.
I PROMISE TO STUBBORNLY
ATTACK MY PROBLEM
OF BEING STUBBORN,
AND I'LL NEVER DO ANYTHING
TO HURT YOU AGAIN.
THAT'S A RELIEF.
YOU CAN START NOW.
AND-1, AND-2.
FLAP THOSE WINGS.
IT'S AMAZING.
I HAVEN'T FELT THIS GOOD
IN YEARS,
AND ALL BECAUSE OF CATNIP.
WHO KNEW?
THANKS, GATOMON.
GO ON.
NO, REALLY, GO ON.
I WANT TO HEAR MORE.
DO YOU GUYS HEAR THAT NOISE?
LET'S CLIMB OUT HERE
WHERE WE CAN GET
A BETTER LOOK.
WHAT IS THAT?
IT CAN ONLY BE ONE THING.
IT HAS TO BE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S BASE.
YOLEI, I'M SORRY
WE DOUBTED YOU EARLIER.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT IS FLYING.
MMM...
HA HA HA!
HE'S ALMOST COMPLETED --
MY ULTIMATE PROGRAM.
WHAT SORT OF EVIL DIGIMON
IS THE EMPEROR GOING TO UNLEASH
ON THE DIGIDESTINED?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."