Cody: WE ALL WENT
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
TO RESCUE BIYOMON.
WE MET STARMON,
A SHERIFF KIND OF DIGIMON,
WHO THREW US IN JAIL WHEN WE
NOTICED HE HAD A DARK RING.
THAT'S WHERE WE FOUND BIYOMON.
WHEN STARMON LEFT,
DEPUTYMON SHOWED UP.
HE LET THE GIRLS OUT
SO HE COULD PLAY CARDS.
STARMON GOT REALLY MAD
AND WENT LOOKING FOR DEPUTYMON.
STARMON CHALLENGED DEPUTYMON
TO A DUEL.
DEPUTYMON GOT BLASTED.
WE MANAGED TO ESCAPE
AND SAVE THE GIRLS
AND DESTROY THE DARK RINGS.
WHAT A ROUNDUP!
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Man: STUDENTS LATE
FOR FIRST PERIOD
WILL BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR CLEANING THE BUBBLE GUM
FROM UNDER THE DESKS
AFTER SCHOOL.
COME ON, KIDS, CHOP-CHOP.
SOMEONE WOKE UP
ON THE WRONG SIDE OF THE BED.
NO KIDDING.
[ Thinking ]
GET YOURSELF TOGETHER.
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
[ Thinking ]
THERE'S KARI.
[ Gasps ]
STAY AWAY!
OH, T.K. SORRY.
OH.
[ Panting ] COME ON, GUYS,
YOU HEARD THE PRINCIPAL.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO SCRAPE GUM, DO YOU?
[ GROANS ]
[ PANTING ]
Davis: LAST ONE IN
HAS TO EAT THE OLD GUM!
SCHOOL -- WOW.
LOOKS LIKE FUN.
I DON'T THINK KARI'S HAVING
FUN INSIDE OF SCHOOL OR OUT.
SHE HASN'T BEEN SLEEPING WELL
'CAUSE OF HER BAD DREAMS.
BAD DREAMS?
YEAH. SHE WON'T TELL ME
WHAT THEY'RE ABOUT,
BUT SHE WAKES UP
EVERY MORNING
DRIPPING
IN A COLD SWEAT.
DOES SHE SENSE SOMETHING?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE I'M JUST IMAGINING IT.
LET'S GO RAID
THE CAFETERIA.
HEY, WAIT FOR ME.
Man: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
AS YOU CAN SEE,
"X" EQUALS "Y,"
"Y" EQUALS 14,
AND LICKETY-SPLIT "Q"
EQUALS 36.
NOW, ISN'T THAT EXCITING?
[ Thinking ]
WHAT'S MORE BORING --
PAINT DRYING OR MATH?
I WONDER WHY KARI'S BEING
SO DISTANT TODAY?
[ Thinking ]
WHAT IS WRONG WITH ME?
AM I JUST OVERTIRED
FROM NOT SLEEPING?
I CAN'T GET THESE DREAMS
OUT OF MY HEAD.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I KNOW MY MATH SCORES HAVE BEEN
A LITTLE FOGGY LATELY,
BUT THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
[ GASPS ]
THIS IS...BIZARRE.
HEY, DID SOMEONE FLOOD
THE BOYS' BATHROOM AGAIN?
WAIT. WHERE AM I?
T.K.? GATOMON?
YOLEI?
TAI!
HUH?
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
KARI!
All: HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH...
KARI!
ARE YOU OKAY, KARI? YOU WANT
TO GO TO THE NURSE'S OFFICE?
YES, SIR.
[ Thinking ] SOMETHING'S
DEFINITELY WRONG WITH HER.
[ Thinking ]
OH, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
BLAME IT ON THE ALGEBRA.
IT WAS SO BORING,
YOU FELL ASLEEP
AND DREAMED
YOU WERE IN THE OCEAN.
I'M NOT GOING CRAZY.
I'M SORRY
I LET YOU DOWN, TAI.
GET A HOLD
OF YOURSELF, KARI.
[ GASPS ]
HELLO?
IS ANYBODY THERE?
DAVIS, IS THAT YOU?
YOU WIN, DAVIS.
I'M SCARED NOW.
[ BREATHING NERVOUSLY ]
[ GASPS ]
GRRAAH.
AAH!
Man: MAY I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION.
WILL THE STUDENT WHO PUT
THE JELLY DONUTS IN THE POOL
PLEASE REPORT TO THE OFFICE.
KARI?
WHA --
EXCUSE ME, NURSE,
MAY I SEE KARI?
Woman: I'M SO SORRY,
BUT KARI'S NOT HERE, SWEETIE.
HOW ABOUT A LOLLIPOP?
HUH?
DO YOU WANT
TO LIE DOWN, T.K.?
MAYBE SHE'S IN THE GIRLS'
BATHROOM. I'LL CHECK.
Girl: AAH!
KARI? SORRY.
SHE'S NOT IN THE LIBRARY.
KARI, ARE YOU DOWN THERE?
KARI!
IT'S LIKE
SHE JUST DISAPPEARED.
[ Thinking ]
SHE MIGHT BE IN TROUBLE.
SHE MIGHT BE IN DANGER.
SHE MIGHT BE --
RIGHT THERE.
[ Thinking ] BOY,
DO I HAVE A HEADACHE.
AND THEN I THREW
THE JELLY DONUTS IN THE POOL.
[ BOYS LAUGHING ]
T.K.: KARI!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT WAS WEIRD.
I WAS AT THE BEACH.
YOU DITCHED SCHOOL?
NO, SILLY -- THE BEACH
IN ANOTHER DIMENSION.
YOU SAW ME IN CLASS.
I WAS JUST SITTING THERE.
THEN THE NEXT THING I KNEW,
I WAS IN THE OCEAN.
NOW YOU'VE TOTALLY
LOST ME.
THEN, ON MY WAY
TO THE NURSE'S OFFICE,
IT HAPPENED AGAIN.
I WAS SURROUNDED BY WATER,
AND THEN I SAW ONE OF THEM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
ONE OF THEM?
DIGIMON. THEY KEEP TRYING
TO TAKE ME TO THEIR WORLD.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN RESIST ANYMORE.
YOU'VE GOT TO!
WHERE ARE THEY, KARI?
WE'LL FIGHT THEM!
I CAN'T, T.K.
I'M SORRY. I'M JUST NOT STRONG
LIKE MY BROTHER TAI.
YOU'RE GOING TO QUIT,
GIVE UP, JUST LIKE THAT?
LOOK, KARI,
I CARE TOO MUCH ABOUT YOU
TO LET ANYONE TAKE YOU
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
UH...
UH, SORRY,
I'D BETTER GO NOW.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER?
Man: WILL MARY ROBERTSON
PLEASE REPORT TO THE OFFICE?
YOUR LOCKER IS MISSING.
THE BEACH.
[ SNORING ]
[ Gasps ] KARI!
Woman: YOU'RE SPEEDING,
HAROLD!
KARI! KARI, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOU?
OH...
[ GASPS ]
WHERE'D SHE GO?
BY INCREASING
THE SYSTEM MEMORY,
I'M EXPANDING THE "D"
TERMINAL'S CAPABILITIES.
[ Sarcastically ] BOY,
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO PARTY.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF WE COULD COMMUNICATE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
NOT JUST THROUGH E-MAIL,
BUT IN REAL TIME, TOO.
IT COULD BE HELPFUL
FOR KEEPING TABS
ON THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
BORING. I'D RATHER GO OUTSIDE
AND PLAY SOME SOCCER.
NO KIDDING.
LET'S GET
SOME FRESH AIR.
THIS PLACE SMELLS LIKE
A PILE OF STALE SWEAT SOCKS.
T.K., WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU LOOK AWFUL.
IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
[ PANTING ]
KARI'S DISAPPEARED.
All: HUH?
[ Thinking ]
IT HAPPENED AGAIN.
I'M BACK AT THE BEACH,
BUT SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
WHAT KIND OF LIGHTHOUSE
SHINES DARK LIGHT?
Davis: THERE'S NO WAY
SHE COULD JUST VANISH
INTO THIN AIR.
SHE'S GOT TO BE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
IT'S NOT THAT EASY. SHE MIGHT
NOT BE IN THE DIGIWORLD.
DID YOU
HIT YOUR HEAD?
UH...
RIGHT NOW, THE SYSTEM CAN'T
EVEN PINPOINT KARI'S LOCATION.
Davis: WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO WASTE ANY MORE TIME.
LET'S GO
AND FIND HER ON OUR OWN.
DAVIS, I DON'T THINK --
NOW'S THE TIME FOR ACTION!
YOLEI, OPEN THE GATE.
WOULD YOU ALL
STOP TALKING?
All: HUH?
IT MAKES NO SENSE
TO OPEN THE GATE
UNTIL WE CAN TARGET
KARI'S EXACT LOCATION.
THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS GIGANTIC,
AND IF WE GO IN THERE
WITHOUT ANY DIRECTION,
WE'RE BOUND
TO GET LOST, TOO.
SHE'S NOT
IN THE DIGIWORLD.
THE BEACH --
THAT'S WHERE SHE IS!
T.K.!
KARI!
THIS PLACE IS CREEPY,
BUT AT LEAST THE BEACH
IS NICE...AND DESERTED.
IT MUST NOT BE
THE TOURIST SEASON.
Patamon:[ Panting ]
T.K., WAIT FOR US!
Gatomon: YEAH, T.K.,
LET US BE YOUR ADVANCEMON.
YOU'RE A LOVER,
NOT A FIGHTER.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
HUH?
I KNEW THERE WAS
SOMETHING WRONG WITH HER.
SHE NEEDED MY HELP,
BUT I LET HER DOWN.
IF I DIDN'T LEAVE HER
BY HERSELF,
NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
COME ON, T.K., LET'S GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
SHE'S NOT THERE.
I SAW HER DISAPPEARING
IN CLASS.
SHE'S IN A DIFFERENT
DIMENSION.
AND THIS STUPID PIECE
OF JUNK IS USELESS.
[ Thinking ] THERE'S NOT EVEN
A HOT DOG STAND ON THIS BEACH.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S A DOORWAY.
MAYBE THAT'S THE WAY
OUT OF THIS STUPID WORLD.
[ DISTANT VOICES ]
Patamon: LOOK, THE NEWS COPTER!
MAYBE ANOTHER HIGH-SPEED CHASE.
I REALLY WISH
WE HAD MORE OF A CLUE
AS TO WHERE SHE WENT.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
SHE KEPT SAYING SOMETHING
ABOUT THE BEACH.
NOW WE'LL NEVER FIND HER!
T.K., DON'T BE
SUCH A SCAREDY-CAT.
HUH?
KARI'S ONE TOUGH KID.
WE HAVE TO BELIEVE
SHE CAN TAKE CARE OF HERSELF
UNTIL WE FIND HER.
YOU'RE RIGHT, GATOMON.
THANKS.
COME ON, LET'S KEEP
LOOKING FOR HER.
HELLO?
IS ANYBODY IN HERE?
ECHO!
[ Thinking ] COMING IN HERE
HAS GOT TO BE THE WORST IDEA
I HAVE EVER HAD.
I MUST BE OUT OF MY MIND.
Voices: KARI.
[ GASPS ]
HELP US! HELP US!
GET BACK!
I PLAY A LOT OF SOCCER,
SO I KNOW HOW TO KICK!
HELP US!
WHAT DO YOU WANT
FROM ME?
I DON'T CARE
WHAT T.K. SAYS.
I KNOW KARI'S
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
AND I'M GOING TO SAVE HER.
HERE I COME, KARI.
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
I JUST CHANGED
THE STUPID BATTERIES.
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
[ GROANS ]
YOU GUYS DON'T LOOK
SO WELL.
[ MOANING ]
SO, WHAT ARE YOU?
ARE YOU DIGIMON?
DIGI...MON?
I DON'T KNOW
IF WE'RE DIGIMON,
BUT I KNOW WE'RE SCUBAMON.
WE HAVE BIG FLIPPERS FOR
SWIMMING DEEP IN THE OCEAN.
WE HAVE NO IDEA
HOW WE GOT DOWN HERE
OR HOW LONG WE'VE BEEN
IN THIS AWFUL TUNNEL.
YOU POOR THINGS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
WE DON'T REMEMBER.
ONE DAY, WE WERE SERVING
OUR UNDERSEA MASTER,
AND THE NEXT MINUTE,
WE WERE HERE,
AND WE FEEL TERRIBLE!
THIS IS AWFUL.
WHO WOULD DO SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
WHY NOT GO BACK
TO THE OCEAN?
I WISH THAT WE COULD.
A DARK MAN CAME
INTO OUR MASTER'S KINGDOM
AND PUT THESE DARK SPIRALS
ON OUR ARMS
THAT STOLE OUR STRENGTH
AND MADE US ALL HIS SLAVES.
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
THAT'S WHY WE SUMMONED YOU.
YOU ARE OUR ONLY HOPE.
HUH?
YOU HAVE TO HELP US.
YOU ARE VERY POWERFUL,
ENOUGH TO FREE US
FROM THE DARK SPIRALS.
WE'VE USED THE LAST
OF OUR STRENGTH
TO GET YOU HERE.
PLEASE HELP US RETURN
TO THE OCEAN
WHERE WE CAN SERVE
OUR MASTER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I COULD
POSSIBLY DO TO HELP.
All: HELP US!
HELP US! HELP US!
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL DO MY BEST,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M STRONG ENOUGH.
[ Thinking ] COME ON, KARI,
STOP DOUBTING YOURSELF.
YOU ARE NOT A QUITTER.
[ MOANING ]
[ GASPS ]
COME ON, EVERYBODY!
WE'VE GOT TO RUN!
LET'S GO!
THE TUNNEL IS COLLAPSING!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
[ COUGHING ]
[ GASPS ]
GRRAAH!
THAT CREATURE IS A SERVANT
OF THE DARK ONE
WHO PUT THESE RINGS
ON US.
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
SPINNING NEEDLE!
WE'RE SITTING DUCKS HERE,
AND I CAN'T FIGHT
WITHOUT MY FRIENDS!
KARI!
I THINK
HE JUST WENT CRAZY.
KARI!
HUH? THEY BOTH FLIPPED.
I FEEL SO HELPLESS.
MY BROTHER WOULD KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
I NEED YOU, TAI...
GATOMON...
THE NATIONAL GUARD!
All: KARI!
[ GASPS ]
T.K.
IT'S HER!
T.K., WAIT!
OH, WHAT THE HECK.
I GOT NINE LIVES.
All: WHOA!
AAH!
T.K., PROMISE ME
WE'LL NEVER DO THAT
EVER AGAIN.
Kari: T.K.! GATOMON!
T.K.: THERE SHE IS!
HEY, GUYS,
I'M RIGHT DOWN HERE!
STAY THERE.
GRRAAH!
TIME TO ROCK, PATAMON!
RIGHT.
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
PATAMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
PEGASUSMON --
FLYING HOPE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GRRAAH!
SPINNING NEEDLE!
PEGASUSMON!
THAT WAS TOO CLOSE!
WIND MANE!
QUICK, KARI! I HAVE
TO ARMOR DIGEVOLVE RIGHT NOW!
BUT I DON'T HAVE
MY "D" TERMINAL.
WE'RE TOAST.
OH, I DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH LONGER THEY CAN LAST.
GRRAAH!
HE'S ON OUR TAIL!
PEGASUSMON!
PEGASUSMON,
THE CONTROL SPIRE --
YOU'VE GOT
TO TAKE IT OUT.
THEN I CAN DIGEVOLVE!
Pegasusmon: HERE GOES
NOTHING!
FULL BLAST, PEGASUSMON!
EQUUS BEAM!
T.K.: NICE SHOOTING,
PEGASUSMON!
GATOMON
DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE.
ANGEWOMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ANGEWOMON!
HMM?
GRRAAH!
EQUUS BEAM!
HEAVEN'S CHARM!
♪ LET'S ALL GO DIGITAL ♪
NICE JOB! THIS BATTLE
WAS JUST A DAY AT THE BEACH.
Kari: ANGEWOMON,
YOU'VE GOT TO HELP THEM.
[ MOANING ]
HA HA HA HA!
HUH?
[ GROANING ]
MUCH BETTER.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A REDEYE REDUCTION.
YOU GUYS ASKED FOR MY HELP,
AND I GAVE IT TO YOU.
NOW WHAT DO YOU WANT?
AAH, DON'T HURT ME!
T.K.: LET HER GO,
YOU CREEPS!
COME WITH US, CHILD.
YOU'LL BE OUR NEW QUEEN.
WE NEED YOU.
I TRUSTED YOU GUYS,
AND YOU LIED TO ME.
AAH!
BUT WE THOUGHT YOU WOULD LOVE
TO BE OUR QUEEN.
WITH YOUR POWER, YOU COULD
LEAD US IN THE BATTLE
AGAINST OUR UNDERSEA MASTER.
BUT I GUESS WE WERE WRONG.
BEWARE, CHILD, OUR MASTER
CAN SENSE YOUR POWER, TOO,
AND HE WILL COME FOR YOU.
I'M READY
TO GO HOME NOW.
IT COULD BE WORSE.
WE COULD BE SCRAPING GUM
AT SCHOOL.
T.K.: LAST ONE HOME
IS A ROTTEN DIGIEGG!
Kari: THANKS FOR COMING
AFTER ME, T.K.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S OKAY, KARI. I KNOW
YOU'D DO THE SAME FOR ME.
HEY, T.K.,
REMEMBER THIS MORNING
WHEN YOU SAID
YOU REALLY CARED FOR ME?
WHAT DID YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
YOU KNOW,
IT WAS JUST...STUFF.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CARE FOR YOU, TOO.
[ BOTH GIGGLE ]
GRRAAH!
WHO IS THIS EVIL
DARK UNDERSEA MASTER?
DON'T MISS THE UPCOMING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."
ALL RIGHT,
YOU READY TO GO?
♪ DIGIMON'S MAKING A SCENE,
THEY'RE KICKING IT UP ♪
♪ KICK IT UP
TO THE BIG SCREEN ♪
♪ DIGIMON'S MAKING A SCENE,
THEY'RE KICKING IT UP ♪
♪ DIGIDUDES WILL DIGIRULE
WITH DIGIABILITY AND DIGITUDE ♪
♪ SAVE THE WORLD
FROM A DIGIDISASTER ♪
♪ THE TRIBE FROM THE NET
MEETS THE DIGITAL MASTERS ♪