WE WERE ALL SURPRISED TO LEARN
THERE WAS A NEW DIGI-EGG
IN AN OIL PLATFORM.
BEFORE WE COULD GET IT OUT,
MEGASEADRAMON TRAPPED US
UNDERWATER.
THE ESCAPE POD ONLY HELD
ONE PERSON.
WE WANTED CODY TO GO FOR HELP.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE US.
WE DIDN'T GIVE HIM A CHOICE.
WE FOUND THE DIGI-EGG WHEN
WHAMON CAME TO OUR RESCUE.
CODY LIFTED THE DIGI-EGG
AND ARMADILLOMON DIGIVOLVED
TO SUBMARIMON.
HE AND IKKAKUMON CERTAINLY
TAUGHT MEGASEADRAMON A LESSON.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
INTO ULTIMATE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
AND HERE WE GO!
AWESOME!
MY NEW TV SHOW,
"WHEN PARAKEETS ATTACK,"
WILL BE A SMASH HIT.
YEAH, YEAH, WHATEVER.
DID YOU CHECK THE CAMERA
BEFORE YOU FILMED THIS FOOTAGE?
OF COURSE.
I'M A PROFESSIONAL.
OKAY, THEN WHAT THE HECK
IS THAT SHADOW?
YAAH!
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
TIME FOR A SNACK!
IS THAT ALL YOU CAN
THINK ABOUT -- FOOD?
TRAVELING TO AND FROM
THE DIGITAL WORLD
CAN WORK UP
QUITE AN APPETITE.
HE'S RIGHT.
WE DESERVE TO CELEBRATE
FOR OUR LATEST VICTORY
OVER THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
PIZZA -- THERE'S A RAD
NEW PLACE BY THE BEACH.
HALF ANCHOVIES,
HALF MUSTARD.
CODY?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NOTHING. I'M JUST NOT SURE
IT'S TIME TO CELEBRATE
WHEN WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR IS UP TO.
MAYBE CODY'S RIGHT.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
HOLD OFF ON THE PIZZA
UNTIL WE CAN FIGURE OUT
OUR NEXT PLAN OF ATTACK.
WE CAN'T FIGHT HIM
ON AN EMPTY STOMACH.
HA HA HA.
YEAH, YEAH!
Cody: STARTING TOMORROW,
WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO USE THIS CLASSROOM.
WHAT? WHY NOT?
THE DETENTION ROOM
HAS BEEN MOVED HERE,
AND ALL THE BAD KIDS
WILL BE PUT
IN THE COMPUTER LAB.
HEY, WE'RE NOT ALL BAD!
HOW CAN WE GO IF WE CAN'T
ACCESS THE COMPUTER LAB?
WAIT A SEC.
WE CAN'T GO
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD
TOMORROW ANYWAY.
WE HAVE BIG PLANS.
WHAT PLANS?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "WE"?
HE MEANS PLANS
WITH ME, DAVIS.
AAH!
ARE YOU TWO TALKING
ABOUT A DATE TOGETHER?
OF COURSE NOT, SILLY.
YOU GUYS HAVE A DATE
TO DO FRACTIONS?
WHAT GIVES?
NO, DAVIS.
THAT'S A DATE, NOT A FRACTION.
TOMORROW MARKS THE ANNIVERSARY
OF WHEN THE DIGIDESTINED
DEFEATED MYOTISMON.
DAVIS THOUGHT
IT WAS A FRACTION.
WELL, HOW SHOULD I KNOW
THEY STARTED PUTTING MATH
IN CALENDARS?
DO YOU WANT
TO COME WITH US?
ON YOUR DATE?
I TOLD YOU,
IT'S NOT A DATE.
DO YOU PROMISE, KARI?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S ALREADY
BEEN FOUR YEARS
SINCE WE WENT
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I CAN'T IMAGINE BEING
IN SUMMER CAMP ONE SECOND,
THEN IN ANOTHER DIMENSION
THE NEXT.
THAT BEATS CANOEING
AND ARCHERY ANY DAY.
I WAS SICK.
I MISSED CAMP THAT SUMMER.
YOU WEREN'T THERE
THE FIRST TIME
WE SAW THE WEIRD STUFF.
WAIT. YOU GUYS LOOK
WEIRD TO US, YOU KNOW.
LOOK, IT'S TAI
AND THE WHOLE GANG.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, GUYS.
HEY!
MIMI.
HI.
WOW,
WHAT A REUNION.
IT HAS BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE'VE ALL
BEEN TOGETHER.
NO KIDDING.
THERE'S ENOUGH OF US HERE
TO START
OUR OWN SOCCER LEAGUE.
NOT ALL THE CORRUPTED DIGIMON
WE ENCOUNTERED WERE IN FACT BAD.
THEY WERE JUST
UNDER THE INFLUENCE
OF THE EVIL BLACK EARS.
WE FOUND OUT WE COULD
DESTROY THE BLACK EARS
WITH OUR DIGIVICES
AND FREE THEM.
THEY BECAME GOOD FRIENDS
AND EVENTUALLY HELPED US
DEFEAT THE FOUR DARK MASTERS.
THOSE DARK MASTERS SOUND
LIKE MY MATH TEACHER.
THEY SHOULD MAKE A MOVIE
OUT OF THIS STORY.
I HOPE THESE GRASS STAINS
WILL COME OUT OF MY CLOTHES
OR MY MOM WILL GROUND ME.
YOU GUYS HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER
NO MATTER WHAT.
REMEMBER THAT FRIENDSHIP
IS THE KEY.
THERE IT IS.
THERE IT IS AGAIN.
THIS IS ABSOLUTELY
IMPOSSIBLE.
I'VE WATCHED THIS
STUPID TAPE 50 TIMES,
AND EVERY TIME, THAT SHADOW
DOES SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
AND THIS WAS MY FIRST TIME
AS A DIRECTOR.
LOOK AT THOSE MONITORS.
IT'S NOT JUST US.
THAT SHADOW IS ON
EVERY PROGRAM
ON THIS TV STATION.
HAVE YOU CHECKED
FOR TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES?
THIS ISN'T TECHNICAL,
BOSS.
THEN WHAT IS IT,
SMART GUY?
A GHOST.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO TELL MY BOSS
I CAN'T GET MY SHOW
ON THE AIR
BECAUSE OF A GHOST?
THEY'LL CAN ME FOR SURE.
I SHOULD HAVE GONE
TO ACCOUNTING SCHOOL.
THAT'S AN INCREDIBLE STORY.
I MUST ADMIT,
I'M AFRAID WE CAN'T LIVE UP
TO THE ACHIEVEMENTS
OF YOU ORIGINAL DIGIDESTINED.
WE WOULDN'T BE HERE
IF WE COULDN'T HANDLE IT.
I'M READY TO FIGHT
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
DAVIS,
YOU'RE SO BRAVE.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT --
TAKE NO PRISONERS.
OH, YEAH?
CAN THE REST
OF YOU HANDLE IT?
I'M NOT SURE.
JUST FOLLOW DAVIS.
AAH!
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
I HAVEN'T BEEN HERE
IN A WHILE.
IT'S THE SAME,
INCLUDING THE SMELL
OF YOUR SOCKS.
I JUST FINISHED
CLEANING THE PLACE.
I SEE.
HOW LONG
HAVE THESE BEEN HERE?
QUIT NITPICKING, T.K.
DAD'S BEEN PUTTING IN
A LOT OF HOURS,
AND I'VE BEEN REHEARSING
WITH MY BAND.
OH, SORRY.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
IT'S JUST YOU TWO GUYS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, THIS PLACE
DOES HAVE A DISTINCT ODOR
TO IT.
THOSE DISHES ARE SO FILTHY,
I'D RATHER FACE
THE DARK MASTERS AGAIN
THAN CLEAN THEM.
IF MOM LIVED WITH ME,
SHE'D NEVER
LET THIS MESS HAPPEN.
YEAH, SHE CRACKS
THE WHIP ON ME.
ANYWAY, I'M STARVING.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO EAT?
AND DON'T EXPECT
ANYTHING FANCY
'CAUSE WE HAVEN'T GONE
GROCERY SHOPPING
IN QUITE A WHILE.
ANYTHING WILL BE FINE.
OKAY, BUT I WARNED YOU.
FIRST I'LL TAKE
A LITTLE STROLL
OVER TO
OUR OLD REFRIGERATOR
AND TAKE A PEEK
AT WHAT'S NOT EXPIRED.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE JUST
ORDER A PIZZA? I'LL BUY.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA,
A REAL HOT ONE.
AHH.
[ GULPING ]
HA HA HA.
QUICK, CALL 911
OR THE POISON CENTER!
I'M GOING TO PASS OUT!
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU,
EAT AT YOUR OWN RISK,
BUT YOU SAID
YOU WERE HUNGRY.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
IT'S A SECRET,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU.
A LITTLE BIT OF HOT SAUCE,
A LITTLE WASABI,
AND A MYSTERY MEAT
I FOUND IN THE REFRIGERATOR
COVERED IN GREEN FUZZ.
I NEVER THOUGHT COOKING
COULD MAKE YOU FEEL DIZZY.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
OH, DAD MUST BE HOME.
HEY, DAD.
HEY, T.K. HEY, MATT.
SORRY I'M LATE AGAIN.
ANOTHER TOUGH DAY
AT THE TV STATION?
IT'S ALWAYS TOUGH,
BUT LATELY
IT'S BEEN JUST BRUTAL.
AHH...
DAD, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO EXPLAIN IT.
MYOTISMON DESTROYED
THE STATION AGAIN.
I ALMOST WISH.
AT LEAST THEN
I WOULD HAVE AN ANSWER
FOR WHAT'S GOING ON.
MY STAFF IS QUITTING
EVERY HOUR,
SAYING THEY'RE SEEING
STRANGE THINGS.
I DON'T BLAME THEM.
I MUST BE LOSING MY MIND.
WHAT'S HAPPENING,
DAD?
ONE SECOND YOU'RE
WALKING DOWN THE HALL
AND YOU SEE
SOMETHING MOVING
OUT OF THE CORNER
OF YOUR EYE.
THAT DOESN'T SOUND
TOO CRAZY SO FAR.
RIGHT, BUT WHEN YOU
TURN TO LOOK...
NOTHING, NOT A TRACE
OF ANYONE OR ANYTHING.
JUST AN EMPTY HALLWAY.
IT MIGHT SOUND CRAZY,
BUT I'VE COME
TO A CONCLUSION --
THE STATION IS HAUNTED.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT
JUST OVERTIRED?
YOU HAVE BEEN PUTTING IN
A LOT OF HOURS.
I KNOW,
BUT IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
FOR INSTANCE,
THERE'S THIS DARK SHADOW.
IT KEEPS APPEARING
ON EVERY MONITOR IN THE STATION,
BUT IT'S DIFFERENT
EVERY SINGLE TIME.
THE EQUIPMENT -- IT PROBABLY
NEEDS TO BE CLEANED.
I KNOW,
I THOUGHT OF THAT.
WOW, THAT'S PRETTY WEIRD.
YOU'RE TELLING ME.
MAYBE IT IS STRESS.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
MAYBE I'LL GO
ON A VACATION.
I HEARD THE ARCTIC
IS A NICE PLACE TO VISIT.
I HAVEN'T TAKEN ONE
IN 15 YEARS.
WHAT'S UP
WITH THE CD PLAYER?
IT'S A SOOTHING RECORDING
OF BUFFALOES MIGRATING.
BUFFALO?
YEAH, I HEARD THESE RECORDINGS
HELP WITH STRESS.
AT THIS POINT,
I'M WILLING TO TRY ANYTHING.
I'M A HAPPY
LITTLE BUFFALO.
YOU'VE FLIPPED YOUR LID.
DON'T MIND HIM, DAD.
HE'S JUST NOT
A HAPPY LITTLE BUFFALO.
[ SIGHS ]
BOY, AM I HUNGRY.
CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT!
THIS IS THE MOMENT
OF TRUTH.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
AAH!
NOT AGAIN!
LOOK, BOSS, WE'RE NEVER
GOING TO FINISH AT THIS RATE.
WE'RE DEFINITELY GOING
TO NEED MORE TIME.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO GO
ON THE AIR TOMORROW!
OH, THAT'S JUST GREAT!
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
MY CAREER IS FINISHED.
I'LL FOREVER BE KNOWN
AS THE HAUNTED DIRECTOR!
WE GOT THE SOUNDTRACK BACK,
BUT IT'S WEIRD.
THIS IS THE VERY WORST DAY
OF MY ENTIRE LIFE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "WEIRD"?
PLAY THE DARN TAPE.
HERE GOES.
[ BREATHING ]
HEY, WAIT,
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING.
WHERE'S THE MUSIC?
THAT'S THE THING --
WE RECORDED THIS MUSIC,
BUT IT PLAYS BACK THIS VOICE.
[ LOW VOICE SPEAKING ]
I DIDN'T SIGN UP
FOR THIS.
IT'S THE GHOST!
IT DOESN'T SOUND HAPPY,
AND I BET IT'S COMING FOR US!
HE COULD BE ANYWHERE.
[ ALL WHIMPERING ]
SIR, WE NEED YOU
RIGHT AWAY.
THE SHADOW?
OH, NO, NOT AGAIN.
HEY, IT'S TOKYO TOWER.
I DID MY FIRST
FASHION SHOOT HERE.
THIS PLACE LOOKS BETTER
THAN THE LAST TIME I SAW IT.
IS IT TRUE
THAT A DIGIMON LEVELED IT?
AND HE ALMOST DEMOLISHED
THE ENTIRE CITY, TOO.
WHY DID HE HAVE TO
DESTROY THE TOWER?
WHY COULDN'T HE HAVE BLASTED
MY DENTIST'S OFFICE INSTEAD?
AND THAT IS HOW WE DETERMINE
HOW FAST THE PIE WAS MOVING
WHEN IT HIT THE CLOWN
IN THE FACE.
[ Thinking ]
PLEASE LET THE BELL RING.
PLEASE GET ME OUT OF HERE.
THE MALL IS CROWDED,
JUST LIKE ALWAYS.
THIS ANNIVERSARY
IS MAKING ME THINK
ABOUT THE DIGIMON WE LOST.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
EVERYWHERE I LOOK TODAY,
I'M SEEING THEIR FACES.
SURE ARE LOTS
OF GOOD MEMORIES.
MM-HMM.
MY MOM IS AT A COOKING
WITH FUNGUS CLASS.
WHILE SHE'S GONE,
I THOUGHT WE COULD
DO AN EXPERIMENT.
WHAT KIND OF EXPERIMENT?
IT'S SIMPLE. IT HAS TO DO
WITH THE DIGIPORT.
DIGIPORT?
BUT HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO
AN EXPERIMENT FROM HERE?
WE ALWAYS HAVE TO USE
THE COMPUTERS
IN THE SCHOOL'S COMPUTER LAB
TO TRAVEL
TO AND FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT WHAT IF WE COULD PROGRAM
OUR D-3 DIGIVICES
TO BE ABLE TO OPEN THE DIGIPORT
FROM OUR HOME COMPUTERS, TOO?
YEAH, BUT THAT'S EASIER
SAID THAN DONE, IZZY.
WHERE DO WE BEGIN?
I HAVE A COUPLE OF THEORIES,
BUT I'M NOT REAL SURE.
COME ON, IZZY.
LET'S HEAR THEM.
HERE'S THE THING --
WE'VE ALWAYS JUST ASSUMED
THE POWER OF THE COMPUTER IS
THE KEY TO OPENING THE DIGIPORT.
MY THEORY IS THAT
THE COMPUTERS ARE INCIDENTAL
AND THAT THE D-3s ARE THE TRUE
POWER OF THE DIGIPORT.
THESE THINGS?
RIGHT.
I'VE SUSPECTED IT
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
BECAUSE I DIDN'T HAVE
ENOUGH PROOF
TO BSOLUTELY SURE.
WITH THE SCHOOL'S COMPUTER LAB
BEING USED FOR DETENTION
AND OUR ACCESS BEING LIMITED,
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
MIGHT DO SOME DAMAGE
WHILE WE'RE LOOKING FOR A WAY
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
THAT'S A REALLY GOOD POINT,
BUT WHERE EXACTLY
ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO OPEN THE DIGIPORT?
RIGHT HERE.
WE'LL OPEN IT UP
SEE, ACCORDING TO MY THEORY,
THE D-3 IS ALL WE'LL NEED
TO OPEN THE PORTAL,
BUT IF I'M WRONG,
IT COULD BE DANGEROUS.
OH.
WHO'S THE FIRST GUINEA PIG?
DAVIS, GIVE IT A TRY.
WHAT? WHO, ME?
NO, HE MEANS THE OTHER BOY
WITH GOGGLES.
OH. WHERE IS HE?
HERE GOES.
DIGIPORT, OPEN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
NICE WORK, IZZY.
LET'S GO THROUGH!
WE NEED TO TEST THE DIGIPORT.
Woman: I'M HOME.
VISITORS?
I'D BETTER MAKE
FUNGUS COOKIES.
WAIT, WE CAN'T GO.
MY MOM'S HOME EARLY.
B-BUT --
SHE SAW OUR SHOES
BY THE DOOR.
IF SHE COMES UP
AND WE'RE GONE, WE'RE TOAST.
TAI IS RIGHT.
AH, MAN!
BUMMER. I WANTED TO SEE
MY THEORY THROUGH.
YOU'LL GET YOUR CHANCE
SOON ENOUGH.
I JUST WISH WE WOULD HAVE
KNOWN ABOUT THIS EARLIER.
YEAH, I KNOW. I SHOULD
HAVE SAID SOMETHING SOONER.
NO NEED TO SWEAT IT.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
NICE WORK, IZZY.
NOW THAT WE KNOW THAT
THE D-3 CAN OPEN THE PORTAL,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BE
EXTRA ESPECIALLY CAREFUL.
BUT WHY?
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
HEY, KIDS.
HI.
HI, MOM.
I HOPE EVERYONE'S HUNGRY!
BECAUSE OF
JUST THAT, KARI.
KEEPING THIS SECRET
FROM OUR FAMILIES
BECOMES A LOT MORE DIFFICULT
WHEN THEY CAN BARGE IN ON US.
I CAN'T IMAGINE IF OUR MOTHER
CAME INTO OUR ROOMS
IN THE NIGHT
AND WE WEREN'T THERE.
SHE'D PROBABLY CALL
THE NATIONAL GUARD.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WORK OUT
SOME SORT OF A PLAN.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
LOOK AT THAT HUGE CLOUD.
DID YOU SEE HOW IT JUST CAME
OUT OF NOWHERE?
THOSE WEATHERMEN
ARE ALWAYS WRONG.
SOMETHING HERE'S NOT RIGHT!
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
WHAT IN THE WORLD? HUH?
NOT AGAIN.
[ SHUDDERING ]
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
Woman: IT'S THE GHOST!
Man: IT'S AFTER US!
GATOMON!
[ LOW VOICE SPEAKING ]
GATOMON.
GATOMON!
[ ALL GASP ]
IT'S THE GHOST!
WHO ARE YOU
GOING TO CALL?
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
AAH!
GATOMON.
WHAT DOES IT WANT?
YOU'RE ASKING ME?
IT WANTS ME.
I'M HERE.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
DAVIS, I THINK
SHE FLIPPED HER LID.
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, NO!
LET'S DO SOMETHING!
ARE YOU SURE
THIS IS A GOOD IDEA?
WE'VE GOT TO SAVE
GATOMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
DEMIVEEMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
VEEMON!
UPAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
ARMADILLOMON!
POROMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
HAWKMON!
GO GET 'EM!
I ASSUME
THAT'S A SERVANT
OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
SENT HERE TO FRIGHTEN US.
HE DOESN'T STAND
A GHOST OF A CHANCE.
GOOD ONE.
READY? HUH?
WAIT. I'M HERE!
[ GHOSTLY NOISES ]
GATOMON.
DON'T MOVE, GUYS.
[ GHOSTLY NOISES ]
GATOMON, RUN FOR IT.
WIZARDMON.
[ ALL GASP ]
GATOMON.
GATOMON,
I'M GLAD YOU'VE COME.
WIZARDMON!
A FRIEND?
I SURE HOPE SO.
WIZARDMON, IT'S GOOD
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I NEED TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING, GATOMON.
WHAT IS IT,
OLD FRIEND?
YOUR GREAT ENEMY,
YOU CANNOT BEAT HIM
AS YOU ARE NOW.
HUH?
DOES HE -- DOES HE MEAN
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
YOUR ENEMY IS NOT ONLY
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
BUT A MUCH GREATER
DARKNESS.
THE DARKNESS,
IT CANNOT BE DEFEATED
WITH STRENGTH ALONE.
YOU MUST RETURN THE ONE
WRAPPED IN DARKNESS
TO HIS TRUE SELF.
WHAT? TRUE SELF?
KINDNESS WILL RELEASE
THE GOLDEN RADIANCE.
I HOPE HE DOESN'T MEAN
WE HAVE TO BE NICE TO KEN.
KINDNESS ALONE
WILL NOT PREVAIL, GATOMON.
THE GOLDEN RADIANCE
IS ALSO NECESSARY.
I SEE. BUT --
YOU DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
YOU MUST HURRY.
GOODBYE, MY FRIEND.
BUT WAIT!
I CAN'T.
GATOMON, BE CAREFUL.
WIZARDMON!
HUH?
I'M SORRY.
[ CRYING ]
WIZARDMON!
HURRY...
[ CRYING ]
GATOMON...
HE CAME BACK TO TELL US.
WHO WAS WIZARDMON ANYWAY?
WE WERE BATTLING A VERY EVIL
DARK DIGIMON NAMED MYOTISMON.
HE WAS ABOUT TO DESTROY KARI
AND GATOMON.
WIZARDMON STEPPED IN THE WAY
OF MYOTISMON'S ATTACK...
AND HE PAID THE ULTIMATE PRICE.
WIZARDMON SACRIFICED HIMSELF
IN ORDER TO SAVE KARI
AND GATOMON,
AND THEY'LL NEVER
FORGET HIM FOR IT.
WILL WE EVER
SEE HIM AGAIN?
I'M SURE WE WILL, KARI.
THAT WIZARDMON,
WHAT A FRIEND.
EVEN FROM BEYOND,
HE STILL GETS TO WATCH OVER ME.
WHAT IS THE SIGNIFICANCE
OF THE GOLDEN RADIANCE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."
--Captions by VITAC--
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
AND THE FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY