Kari: THE ONLY WAY WE COULD
STOP KEN WAS TO DEFEAT AGUMON.
WE FOUND
THE DIGI-EGG OF FRIENDSHIP.
FLYMON FOUND US
AND CAPTURED PATAMON.
WE CHASED HIM, BUT IT LED US
RIGHT INTO METALGREYMON
WITH KEN RIDING THE CONTROLS.
GARURUMON ARRIVED
AND FREED PATAMON,
BUT NO ONE COULD REMOVE
THE DARK SPIRAL
FROM METALGREYMON.
DAVIS WAS STILL
HAVING A PROBLEM
FIGHTING HIS DIGIMON FRIEND,
BUT WE CONVINCED HIM
THAT SOMETIMES
FRIENDS HAVE TO MAKE SACRIFICES
FOR THE SAKE OF FRIENDSHIP.
THEN THE DIGI-EGG OF FRIENDSHIP
ACTIVATED.
RAYDROMON DESTROYED
THE DARK SPIRALS
ON METALGREYMON AND ALLOWED HIM
TO DIGIVOLVE BACK INTO AGUMON.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ SHRIEKS ]
SORA!
HUH?
UH, NICE SERVE, GWEN.
I'M FEELING A LITTLE DIZZY.
I'D BETTER TAKE A BREAK.
WHATEVER.
ACTUALLY, WHY DON'T
YOU TWO PLAY?
HUH?
[ Thinking ]
BIYOMON'S IN TROUBLE,
BUT HOW WILL I GET
TO THE DIGIWORLD?
SORA!
HMM.
I'VE GOT
TO TELL THE OTHERS.
[ Thinking ]
THAT CATNIP RINSE
MAKES MY EARS
LOOK TOO STIFF.
SO, READY TO GO?
ROME WASN'T BUILT
IN A DAY.
LOOKING BEAUTIFUL
TAKES TIME.
SO, BEAUTIFUL, CAN YOU
HELP ME WASH THE DISHES?
TIME'S UP.
WHY ARE YOUR EARS
STANDING UP?
IT'S A NEW LOOK. IT'S QUITE
THE RAGE IN KATMANDU.
YOU KNOW, MOST CATS
LIKE MICE, NOT MOUSSE.
[ SNORING ]
Davis: OH,
MY STOMACH IS FULL.
YOU SHOULDN'T EAT SO MUCH
IN THE MORNING.
YOU ATE
TWICE AS MUCH AS ME.
IF YOU KEEP IT UP, YOU'LL
DIGIVOLVE INTO HEAVYMON.
HUH?
BIYOMON.
AN EMERGENCY CALL
FROM BIYOMON? WHAT'S UP?
IT'S BIYOMON.
SHE NEEDS OUR HELP.
THAT'S NOTHING
TO SHAKE A STICK AT.
NOTE TO SELF --
THINK OF BETTER WAY
TO SNEAK UPAMON
OUT OF APARTMENT.
WHOA!
HEY!
Yolei: BE MORE CAREFUL
NEXT TIME.
CODY, WHAT HAVE YOU
BEEN EATING LATELY?
YOU MUST'VE GAINED
20 POUNDS.
IT'S UPAMON.
YOU ATE UPAMON?
SORA SENT AN E-MAIL SAYING
BIYOMON'S IN TROUBLE.
Upamon: [ SQUAWKS ]
YOUR TUMMY'S GROWLING.
Cody: THE ONLY WAY
NOT TO LOOK SUSPICIOUS
IS TO SNEAK QUIETLY.
RIGHT.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
WHERE'S T.K. AND KARI?
IT WASN'T MY TURN
TO WATCH THEM.
NO T.K. OR KARI?
EVEN IF THEY WERE OUT OF TOWN,
AT LEAST THEY'D E-MAIL US.
Kari: HMM, THAT MILK SHAKE
WAS REALLY GOOD,
BUT SEEING YOU DRINK THROUGH
A STRAW WAS EVEN BETTER.
MMM...
NOW WE CAN TAKE
SOME PICTURES.
NO, WAIT.
THE FISH MARKET'S CALLING
MY NAME -- GATOMON!
ALL RIGHT.
[ SNORING ]
HMM, MAYBE THEIR BATTERIES
ARE DEAD.
Davis: MAYBE T.K. DECIDED
TO WASH IN THE BATHTUB.
Sora: WE CAN'T WAIT.
BIYOMON NEEDS US.
WE'LL HAVE TO GO
WITHOUT THEM.
LET'S SEE WHERE BIYOMON'S
DISTRESS SIGNAL CAME FROM.
THERE IT IS. GOT IT!
Davis: WELL, NOW THAT WE KNOW
WHERE WE NEED TO GET,
LET'S GET TO GETTING
TO IT, GOT IT?
All: RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE!
DIGIPORT OPEN!
Hawkmon: OH, VULGAR!
I SENSE THIS PLACE
IS A CULTURAL DESERT!
Armadillomon: I DON'T KNOW.
THIS SANDBLASTING
SURE MAKES MY SHELL
LOOK REAL SHINY.
All: WHOA! AAH!
HMM.
Davis: WOW, CHECK IT OUT!
LOOKS LIKE THE OLD WEST!
Cody: WHERE'S THAT SPIRE
WE SAW ON THE MONITOR?
Sora: I DON'T SEE
A CONTROL SPIRE ANYWHERE!
Davis: WELL,
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
Hawkmon: FEAR NOT, YOLEI,
FOR I WILL GUARD YOU
FROM WHATEVER DANGER
MAY BE THRUST UPON US.
Yolei: INSTEAD, TRY FINDING US
SOME COLD WATER.
HUH? WHERE'S BIYOMON?
Sora: SHE CAN'T HAVE
GONE FAR, DAVIS.
SHE'S HERE SOMEWHERE. WHERE'S
THAT MUSIC COMING FROM?
Cody: IT'S COMING
FROM OVER THERE!
Veemon: LAST ONE THERE'S
A GILA MONSTER!
Davis: HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
IT'S JUST A PLAYER PIANO.
I'M STARTING TO THINK
THERE'S NOBODY HERE.
Voice: YOU'RE
AT THE RIGHT PLACE.
YOU'RE SURE
TO BE HAPPY HERE,
SO SAYS THE 'MON
BEHIND THE STAR.
HOWDY. WELCOME, DIGIPILGRIMS,
TO THE SAFEST TOWN
WEST OF SIRIUS.
THEY CALL ME STARMON.
Hawkmon: STARMON IS
A LAW AND ORDER DIGIMON
WHO KEEPS THE PEACE,
BUT IF YOU BREAK THE LAW,
HIS POWERFUL METEOR SHOWER
WILL RAIN DOWN SWIFT JUSTICE
UPON YOU.
BELLY-UP TO THE BAR
SO I CAN WELCOME YOU
WITH A COLD MUG
OF WELCOME MILK.
THIS IS JUST MY WAY OF BEING
NEIGHBORLY TO STRANGERS.
SO, HERE'S TO YOU!
WHAT IS WELCOME MILK?
IT'S 100% HOMOGENIZED
MOO JUICE, LITTLE MISSY.
HA HA HA. WELCOME!
[ GULPING ]
AHH...
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
I'M KIND OF THIRSTY.
Yolei: MY MOUTH FEELS LIKE
A CLOTHES DRYER
FULL OF COTTON BALLS.
Armadillomon: MY TONGUE
IS A DUSTY TANK TREAD.
All: THANK YOU!
[ GULPING ]
HUH. TOURISTS.
YOU GOT TO LOVE THEM.
HUH?
UH, MR. STARMON,
HAVE YOU BY ANY CHANCE
SEEN A CUTE, LITTLE, PINK,
BIRD-LOOKING DIGIMON
NAMED BIYOMON AROUND HERE?
HMM. DID YOU SAY "BIYOMON"?
THAT KIND OF RINGS A BELL.
YUP. YUP.
I'VE GOT A FEELING I'VE HEARD
THAT DESCRIPTION BEFORE.
BIYOMON WANTED?
WHAT DID SHE DO?
WELL, THAT DIGIDESPERADO
IS ON THE RUN
FROM THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
HE'S GOT A REWARD OUT
FOR HER,
BUT THEY HAVEN'T
CAUGHT HER YET.
WELL, SHE'S HOPEFULLY
SOMEWHERE SAFE BY NOW,
BUT I'LL STILL FEEL BETTER
WHEN WE FIND HER.
MR. STARMON, SIR,
MAYBE YOU COULD HELP.
WE HEARD SHE WAS LAST SEEN
NEAR HERE.
YOU COULDN'T BE
MORE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
AND IF BIYOMON WERE
IN TROUBLE, YOU'D HELP HER.
BEING A LAWMON, I KNOW
YOU'D PROTECT HER
FROM THAT DIGITAL
EMPEROR, RIGHT?
MA'AM, THERE'S SOMETHING
I GOT TO TELL YOU.
All: [ Gasp ]
HE'S WEARING A DARK RING!
WELL, I KNEW THAT
BEHIND THAT TIN STAR
WAS JUST A GUTLESS LOWLIFE
LACKEY OF THE EMPEROR.
YOU COULD'VE TOLD US,
AND WHAT DID WE SAY
ABOUT NAME-CALLING?
THINK HE'S A BAD APPLE
OR A GOOD ONE?
PEOPLE ARE LIKE MILK.
THEY CAN TURN BAD.
YOU MIGHT THINK I'M LOWER
THAN A SNAKE'S BELLY
FOR SAYING THIS,
BUT I DO WORK FOR THE EMPEROR,
AND I GOT ORDERS.
HUNT THEM DOWN
AND PUNISH THE DIGIDESTINED!
WHAT'S THAT EARTH REJECT
DOING NOW --
PULLING THE WINGS
OFF BUTTERFLIES?
YOU CAN BET
HE'S EXPERIMENTING
WITH SOMETHING EVIL.
IT'S ALMOST FINISHED.
HEH HEH HEH!
EARTH REJECT!
I'LL HAVE TO USE THAT
AT THE NEXT COMPANY PICNIC
AND TEAM BUILDING SEMINAR!
HUH?
DON'T THAT BEAT ALL --
TRYING TO ESCAPE?
RUN! RUN!
NO USE TRYING
TO HIGHTAIL IT OUT OF HERE!
TIME FOR A WEATHER REPORT!
METEOR SHOWER!
AAH! AAH!
Davis: I'VE HEARD
OF HEAVY SHOWERS,
BUT THAT WAS TOO MUCH!
NOW YOU'LL ENJOY YOUR STAY!
HEH HEH HEH!
HERE'S THE RULES --
NO COOKIES IN YOUR CELL,
NO LOUD MUSIC AFTER 8:00,
AND NO SHUCKING OYSTERS
DURING MONTHS
WITHOUT AN "R."
NO WAY!
SORA.
All: HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
SORA.
BIYOMON!
I TRIED TO GET AWAY,
BUT I JUST DIDN'T HAVE
THE STRENGTH.
SHH. DON'T TALK.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU JUST SAID, "DON'T TALK,"
DIDN'T YOU?
I WISH YOU WOULD
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
OKAY. YOU CAN TALK
A LITTLE.
WHEN I FIRST CAME HERE
TO THIS TOWN,
I HAD NO IDEA THAT IT WAS UNDER
THE CONTROL OF THE EMPEROR.
I HAD BEEN SHOT DOWN
BY HIS FLYING DRAGONS
AND NEEDED FOOD.
I WAS TIRED, HUNGRY,
AND VERY THIRSTY.
WELCOME, STRANGER.
HUH?
YOUR THROAT
MUST BE PARCHED.
HOW ABOUT A COLD DRINK
OF MILK?
I AM THIRSTY. THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY.
Starmon: METEOR SHOWER!
HEH HEH HEH!
AAH! OH, NO! AAH!
GLAD YOU COULD STAY
A WHILE. HEH HEH HEH!
Veemon: V-HEAD BUTT!
[ GROANS ]
I GUESS I USED TOO MUCH "V"
AND NOT ENOUGH HEAD BUTT.
NICE TRY, BUDDY.
THAT WALL'S AS HARD
AS HIS HEAD AND JUST AS THICK.
YOU SAID IT.
BUT IT SHOULD BE EASY FOR YOU
TO DRILL THROUGH THAT WALL.
DIGIVOLVE INTO DIGMON.
I'M TOO WEAK TO DO IT.
I FORGOT.
WE HAVEN'T EATEN.
I COULD DO SOMETHING
IF I HAD FOOD.
I WISH I HAD SOME SNACKS
FROM YOUR STORE, YOLEI.
Yolei: I'LL CALL MY DAD.
HE DELIVERS.
Hawkmon: BUT WE'RE IN PRISON
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
Veemon: IF IT'S
MORE THAN 5 MILES,
THERE'S
A DELIVERY CHARGE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE A HORSE!
All: HUH?
HE NEEDS
SOME NEW SHOES.
Voice: I SAID WHOA!
NEVER FEAR. THE PROTECTOR
OF JUSTICE IS HERE.
HOLY GUACAMOLE!
JUST WHO IN TARNATION ARE YOU?
HOWDY, FOLKS.
Armadillomon: DEPUTYMON
IS A BARREL-CHESTED DIGIMON
THAT SHOOTS FROM THE LIP,
BUT USUALLY
HE'S HELPFUL AND HARMLESS.
All: HMM.
FROM THE LOOK
ON YOUR FACES,
I FEEL LIKE I SQUASHED
YOUR FAVORITE HAT.
WHAT'S THE STORY?
WE GOT PUT IN THIS JAIL
FOR DOING NOTHING
BY YOUR PARTNER STARMON.
WHERE'S YOUR JUSTICE?
THAT'S ALL
THAT'S IN HERE -- JUST US!
SO, LET'S SEE IT. WHERE'S
YOUR DARK RING, DEPUTY?
I AIN'T GOT NO RING.
NOBODY CONTROLS ME,
NOT EVEN MYSELF!
Veemon: THERE'S NO
DARK RING!
RIGHT-O,
YOU VARMINTS.
Yolei: WE'RE SORRY TO BE
SO SUSPICIOUS OF YOU,
BUT PUT YOURSELF
IN OUR BOOTS.
THERE. DO YOU SEE
ANY RINGS NOW?
All: [ GASP ]
Deputymon: GOT CARRIED AWAY.
WE DIDN'T SEE A THING.
ARE YOU HERE TO KEEP US
IN JAIL OR TO SET US FREE?
NO NEED TO FRET, LADY.
SOON YOU'LL BE FREE.
All: YAY!
Deputymon: COURSE,
I'M ONLY FREEING THE GIRLS.
I NEED CARD PLAYERS,
BUT NOT BOYS
'CAUSE THEY CHEAT.
SAY WHAT?
Veemon: DID I MENTION
I DON'T EVEN CHEAT
AT SOLITAIRE?
STRICTLY WOMENFOLK,
AND THAT'S FINAL.
DIDN'T YOU EVER HEAR
OF WOMEN, CHILDREN,
AND DIGIMON FIRST?
Cody: COULDN'T YOU LET US GO
JUST FOR THE FUN OF IT?
COME ON, LADIES ONLY.
SCOOT!
WHAT IS THIS --
THE PETRIFIED DESERT?
I SAID SCOOT!
Digimon: BUT WE'RE NOT BOYS!
Deputymon: GIDDYAP,
CELLOPHANE!
[ NEIGHS ]
[ HUMMING ]
WELL, IT'S LUNCHTIME.
BEING A RUTHLESS VILLAIN
SURE WORKS UP AN APPETITE.
AND AFTER LUNCH,
A LITTLE NAP,
SO I'LL BE
MY MEAN OLD SELF AGAIN.
HEH HEH HEH!
WHAT? THEY'RE GONE!
DEPUTYMON FREED THE GIRLS,
SAYS BOYS CHEAT AT CARDS.
I IMAGINE THEY'RE ENJOYING
SOME DELICIOUS SNACKS
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
THAT'S IT!
I'M GOING TO LET
THAT POP GUN HAVE IT
WITH BOTH BARRELS!
[ Sighs ]
JUST LOOK AT THAT.
AT WHAT?
HIS LUNCH.
IF I COULD JUST WRAP MY LIPS
AROUND THAT LUNCH,
I COULD ARMOR DIGIVOLVE.
I GOT AN IDEA.
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
PRETEND THAT THESE ROPES
AROUND US ARE PASTA,
AND HELP YOURSELF
TO ALL YOU CAN EAT.
I JUST LOVE CARDS --
CREDIT CARDS, GREETING CARDS,
YOU NAME IT!
AFTER A COUPLE OF HANDS,
LET'S TRY TO ESCAPE.
MAYBE WE COULD GET HIM
TO FALL ASLEEP
BY TALKING HIM
INTO PLAYING CANASTA.
EVER PLAY 52 PICKUP?
AH, SKIP IT.
AND NOW,
LADIES AND GENTLEMON,
WELCOME TO THE WORLD
CHAMPIONSHIP OF OLD MAID.
WINNER TAKE ALL!
AH, COME ON. LET'S HEAR IT!
Sora and Yolei:
[ Unenthusiastically ] YAY!
DO YOU KNOW ANY WAYS
OF CHEATING
WHEN IT COMES
TO PLAYING OLD MAID?
Veemon: I ALMOST GOT IT,
DAVIS.
THERE!
NOW TO FIGURE A WAY
TO BREAK OUT!
CHOCOLATE ALWAYS WORKS.
Cody: WELL, THAT DOES IT.
WE'RE FREE.
DELICIOUS ROPES.
ALL RIGHTY, YOU'RE FIRST,
AND DON'T TRY ANYTHING TRICKY
OR NO FRUIT CUP,
YOU HEAR?
HUH?
STARMON!
WELL, IF IT AIN'T
THAT NAMBY-PAMBY POOR EXCUSE
FOR A SIDEKICK -- DEPUTYMON!
PLAYING WITH THE GIRLS AGAIN,
GEORGIE-PORGIE?
STOP THAT TALK.
YOU GOT NO RIGHT.
FOR ONCE, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE TIME FOR TALKING IS OVER.
LET'S SETTLE THIS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
GOTCHA! COME TO PAPA!
NICE.
THOSE ROPES WERE JUST
A HIGH-FIBER APPETIZER.
NOW, BON APPéTIT.
LOOKS MIGHTY TASTY.
OH, BOY.
YOU KNOW, THE EASIEST WAY
OUT OF HERE IS TO DIG OUT.
YOU'LL HELP OUT LATER.
YOU CAN HAVE SOME.
GREAT.
JUST THIS ONCE, IT'S OKAY
TO GULP YOUR FOOD.
WE GOT TO HELP OUR FRIENDS.
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER!
COOL!
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S MOVE IT!
Davis: YOU GOT IT!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
VEEMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
RAYDROMON --
THE STORM OF FRIENDSHIP!
Deputymon: THIS GHOST TOWN
ISN'T BIG ENOUGH
FOR BOTH OF US,
EVEN IF WE HAD IT ON.
I SAW A MOVIE LIKE THIS ONCE.
THE GOOD GUY WON.
WHICH ONE'S GOOD?
Starmon: TAKE THREE PACES,
THEN TURN AROUND AND FIRE.
1...2...
GO WHOEVER!
2 7/16...AND...
HEY!
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'VE ALREADY TURNED AROUND.
HOLD IT! GOOD GUYS
AREN'T SUPPOSED TO CHEAT!
I'M NOT THAT GOOD.
BESIDES, I'VE NEVER WON
AT NOTHING.
BUT TODAY --
WIN, LOSE, OR DRAW --
I'M COMING OUT OF THIS
A WINNER.
THIS IS BECOMING
A BATTLE OF WITS,
AND DEPUTYMON'S
OUT OF AMMUNITION.
SEMI-GOOD ALWAYS TRIUMPHS
OVER EVIL.
SO GO AHEAD, STARMON,
GIVE ME YOUR BEST SHOT.
FINE. LET'S JUST SEE HOW
THE FORTUNE COOKIE CRUMBLES!
METEOR SHOWER!
WHOA! LET'S MOVE!
AAH!
OH...
WELL, I DROPPED HIM
LIKE A BAD HABIT.
LOOKS LIKE ONE DOWN
AND TWO TO GO.
NOT QUITE.
WHAT SHE SAID.
Davis: HOLD ON!
I'LL HANDLE THIS!
THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG!
METEOR SHOWER!
TOO MUCH CHOCOLATE!
I'LL TRY TO CUT BACK.
DAVIS, DIGIVOLVE ME
INTO FLAMEDRAMON.
HE'S A BETTER FIGHTER!
RIGHT, VEEMON!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
VEEMON,
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
STARMON, YOU'RE FIRED!
FIRE ROCKET!
AAH!
Armadillomon: LOOK!
A CONTROL SPIRE!
LET'S GO!
AAH!
YAHOOEY!
Davis: YOUR TOWN WON'T BE
UNDER THE EMPEROR'S CONTROL
ANYMORE.
Starmon: I GUESS
I JUST WENT PLUMB LOCO.
HOPE THERE'S NO
HARD FEELINGS, BIYOMON.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO APOLOGIZE.
I'M JUST GLAD THAT THINGS
ARE...NORMAL NOW.
Deputymon: YOO-HOO!
TARNATION! IT'S GOOD
THAT I CAUGHT YOU.
YOU DIDN'T THINK ALL OF YOU
WERE GOING TO SKEDADDLE
WITHOUT US SAYING ADIOS
AND PLAYING SOME MORE CARDS,
DID YOU?
All: WE WOULDN'T DO THAT!
[ Sigh ]
Sora: SO WHAT
HAVE YOU GOT, CODY?
I GOT A PAIR OF ACES
AND ANOTHER PAIR OF ACES.
THAT BEATS US ALL.
WE'RE SWITCHING
TO MY FAVORITE CARD GAME --
GO FISH!
All: GO FISH?
[ Sigh ]
HMM, THOSE DIGIDIMWITS
HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I HAVE UP MY SLEEVE.
WHAT WILL
THE DIGITAL EMPEROR DO
TO RAISE THE STAKES EVEN HIGHER
FOR THE DIGIDESTINED?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."