CODY: We hid the fifth
Destiny Stone from Arukenimon
and Mummymon, but
BlackWarGreymon found it easily
and blasted it.
TK had another meltdown.
He once had to watch
Patamon get destroyed
and he's never gotten over it.
The sixth Destiny Stone
was at the bottom of the ocean,
but BlackWarGreymon
got to that one too.
Even though I couldn't hurt him
because he had a heart,
I still stood up to him
and said if you want to destroy
the Destiny Stone,
you'll have to destroy me first!
That's the last time
I try that one.
Luckily Angemon saved me
before BlackWarGreymon
smashed the Destiny Stone.
Now there's only one left!
♪ Digi, Digi, Digi ♪
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Change into
digital champions ♪
♪ To save the digital world ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
NARRATOR: Digivolve
into champions!
Armor Digivolve!
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
♪ Digimon ♪
DAVIS: Dudes,
we can't just stand around.
There's only one
Destiny Stone left.
We gotta find it before
BlackWarGreymon does
and totally loses his cool!
KARI: Yeah, well,
I'm gonna lose my cool
if you keep calling me "dude".
( gasping )
( indistinct chatter )
Looks like Ken has to help
his mother clean.
He says go on ahead without him
and he'll join up with us
when he finishes
vacuuming the chimney.
But what happened to Cody?
Do you think he got
pushed in a locker?
I hope not.
Sorry I'm late.
Well?
We were worried about you.
I was helping clean up
the teachers' lunch room.
It was my turn.
You should be helping us
find the last Destiny Stone!
I mean, between you and Ken,
we must be running
a cleaning service here!
Sheesh, talk about
getting dramatic.
Yolei?
Right, Digiport, open!
We can't waste any time!
Let's go!
( upbeat music )
My mission is clear.
That Destiny Stone
is here somewhere,
and I'm going to find it
if I have to
destroy everything in my path!
Now, where is it?
( grunts )
Black Tornado!
Why can't you be
as powerful as him, Mummymon?
Huh?
But I've got charm and class!
Come on, don't tell me
you're falling for that
prefabricated hunk of shrapnel.
I don't have time to bother
with all that nonsense!
I'm glad,
that's such a big relief.
( horn honking )
Where is it?
I still don't see it.
I should just destroy
everything here.
Where'd he go?
Uh‐oh.
Oh, if we don't get moving,
that bucket of bolts
is going to incinerate us!
Wake up, Mummymon, I need you!
( sighing )
I thought you'd never
come around, give us a kiss.
Anyone ever tell you
you have bad breath?
Why, that's impossible.
I think I brushed my teeth
at least a year ago.
Huh?
( shouting )
( screaming )
Face it, the guy's not
a rocket scientist.
BlackWarGreymon will never
find us in this place.
Mmm.
( gong ringing )
Huh?
Oh.
Huh.
Hmm.
♪
What you want is some
delicious Chinese soup.
Oh, come on,
try it, you'll like it,
it's my specialty.
Egg drop, haha!
ARUKENIMON: Well, I suppose
I could do a bit of shopping
while I'm here in Chinatown.
What I really need
is a nice pair of sandals.
Hmm.
That could be hard, considering
you have eight sticky feet.
They're nice!
Well, I don't need
any comments from you,
sticky tape boy.
You know that I'm sensitive
about my feet.
I'm a spider.
I'm just giving you
a compliment, I love your feet!
Even your pointy toes!
Enough with the feet!
Hey, what's that tasty aroma?
Yum!
( gasping )
It's incredible, what is it?
Mmm.
Chinese soup!
Let's go and get some!
Good idea, maybe we can
even get some extra hot soup
to go and give it
to BlackWargreymon
so he can scald
his mouth when he eats it!
When you're hot, you're hot.
Gee, I hope they
have fortune cookies,
they're my favorite.
So, what'll it be?
I'm Tapirmon,
and I'll be your waiter.
You better leave me a big tip
or next time you'll have
a fly in your wonton.
Huh?
Want some soup?
It's our specialty.
Yeah, extra flies for me!
Just hers.
Finally, a customer!
Uh‐oh, BlackWarGreymon's
in close range!
I hope Ken put away his dust rag
and is able to find us.
Give Ken a break.
After all, cleanliness
is next to diginess!
Okay.
YOLEI: Hey, Kari,
want some mineral water?
Sure, thanks!
Mineral water, huh?
Gee, Yolei, since when
did you get so healthy?
Since our family started
selling it in our store.
It's full of vitamins
and minerals for good health.
Next time you're in
my family's grocery store,
be sure to pick up
a bottle or two.
That's right.
What is this, a commercial?
Yolei!
( laughing )
Ever since those guys
have been able to DNA Digivolve,
they've become
much closer friends.
Don't worry.
Soon you'll DNA Digivolve
with the best of 'em.
Think so?
Patamon and Armadillomon
have been practicing hard
and they're about to master it
at any moment.
Arma‐pat!
Pata‐arm!
( laughing )
( sniffing )
Hey, check out that
scrumptious smell.
Huh?
Hmm.
Mmm, that's awesome!
My stomach is growling
with sheer delight.
( groaning )
Mine's growling
with sheer hunger!
Mine too.
Well, I'm not gonna
pass on good food
and besides, it's not
often we find ourselves
in Digi‐Chinatown,
so we may as well enjoy it.
Right now?
Yes!
Maybe we should
all go in together
for the lunch special.
That way you get
a lot more food!
I want mine as spicy as they
can make it, so watch out!
Cody?
Is there something the matter?
Aren't you hungry?
BlackWarGreymon
is out there looking for
the last Destiny Stone,
like we should be!
Instead, they're all
in there, eating.
Stuffing themselves
with egg foo young!
‐ But Cody.
‐ Huh?
Thing is, I love egg foo young.
Huh?
Armadillomon.
I have a bad feeling that
the reason you and Patamon
haven't been able
to DNA Digivolve is because
I'm too serious all of the time.
But I'll try to lighten up
by the time dessert comes.
I have to say,
this soup is magnificent.
And full of flies,
it's the best!
Waiter!
Need something, sir?
Tell me, my good mon.
What is this tasty soup made of?
Lots of noodles.
Well, I know that.
What else?
Even more noodles.
This isn't getting us
anywhere at all!
This guy's got
noodles on the brain.
I want to talk to your manager.
Of course.
I'm the owner, Digitamamon.
What's the problem?
ARUKINEMON: That stupid waiter
wouldn't tell us
what this delicious soup
is made of.
Sorry, it's a secret recipe.
What?
If I told you my recipe,
it wouldn't be a secret
anymore, now, would it?
What insolence!
Do you have any idea
who you're talking to, buster?
‐ More guests!
‐ Huh?
( gasping )
BOTH: Oh, rats, those kids!
( grunts )
Digitamamon?
It's nice to see you again, but
I've kinda lost my appetite.
Ah, don't worry about it.
Just remember,
there's always takeout.
When you're feeling better,
you have a little mushu.
Maybe a little pupu,
or just for fun,
I'll even throw in
some almond cookies.
How about a nice trip
to the moon?
Would you like that?
( ominous music )
( laughing )
Ready?
( laughing evilly )
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
NARRATOR: Digivolve
into champions!
Veemon, digivolve to...
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
Exveemon!
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
Hawkmon, digivolve to...
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
Aquilamon!
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
Patamon, digivolve to...
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
Angemon!
♪ Digimon, Digimon ♪
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
Armadillon, digivolve to...
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
Ankylomon!
♪ Digital monsters, Digimon ♪
Digiarmor, energize!
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon are the champions ♪
Gatomon, armor digivolve to...
Armor digivolve.
Nefertimon, Angel of Light!
♪ Digital monsters, digimon ♪
Blast Rain!
Queen Claw!
Acid Mist!
( shouting )
( laughing )
Snake Bandage!
( gasping )
DNA Digivolve!
I can't, Stingmon's not here!
I forgot!
What happened to Ken,
did he decide to become a maid?
We'll bust up and then
take them both down.
Yeah.
Digimon, Digimon.
Aquilamon!
Gatomon!
BOTH: DNA Digivolve to...
Huh?
Let's try again.
Right.
Digimon, Digimon.
Aquilamon!
Gatomon!
BOTH: DNA Digivolve to...
Well, this proves one theory.
Digimon have to have
plenty to eat
before they're able
to DNA Digivolve.
We'd better think
of something real fast!
I'm, I'm thinking!
( laughing evilly )
Let's get out of here!
We de‐digivolved,
what happened?
What's in that soup?
They won't get away with this!
KEN: Something's up.
Hurry, let's go!
STINGMON: Right.
Hey, what happened?
I'm not sure,
but if I were you,
I wouldn't order the soup.
I don't get it.
What are we waiting for?
Let's follow 'em!
Yeah!
‐ CODY: No, wait.
‐ Huh?
We should be focused
on what's most important,
and chasing them isn't what
we need to be concerned with.
Right now we all have
to replenish our energy.
That way, we can
DNA Digivolve and get ready
to meet BlackWarGreymon!
I could use a snack.
What do you say?
Let's have something to eat!
Cody's right.
Hey, dudes,
I'm not complaining.
VEEMON AND PATAMON:
We need food, let's eat!
Mm‐hmm.
Wait, we don't have
anyone to cook for us.
‐ Digitamamon left.
‐ Oh, no!
We're not helpless,
we'll cook for ourselves!
We'll do our share
and set the table!
Hey, we can add some onions
and mushrooms.
How about some tuna fish?
How do you turn on the stove?
( laughter )
( sighing )
What's the matter?
( sighs )
( backfires )
I don't know,
it can't be the radiator.
I just put water in it
five years ago.
Lovely.
( groaning )
The only thing that'll
save it now is water!
( shouting )
( coughing )
I'm coming too!
Mummymon, where are you?
This isn't funny at all!
Mummymon!
‐ Quiet!
‐ ( screams )
What's the big idea, you twit?
Shh.
Huh?
Hmm.
( water dripping )
I can hear it.
What is it?
Water dripping.
Oh?
( water dripping )
You're right, Drippy!
The sound's coming
from over there.
Hey, wait for me!
MUMMYMON: We're almost there,
just a little farther.
( panting )
ARUKINEMON: Oh,
great, a swimming pool.
I'm going to stink after this.
( panting )
Oh, that smells
good enough to eat!
What is it?
That sign over there says
it's the Chinese soup spring.
We're looking at
a jumbo pot of soup.
This is where that
irresistible soup was made,
and my stomach's telling me
I've gotta have some!
( laughing )
No slurping!
( groans )
What, don't you
have any manners?
No slimy tongues
allowed in the soup!
( screams )
What's the big deal?
Is there a law against
drinking soup around here?
As a matter of fact, there is!
ARUKINEMON: "Drinking this soup
is strictly forbidden
and you don't want
to know the consequences." Hmm.
That's baloney,
it makes me want to
have some of it even more!
And you're not gonna stop me.
( groaning )
Yummy.
( chuckles )
( slurping )
Mmm.
Ahh.
( rumbling )
Oh!
I hope that's not
a giant fly seeking revenge.
( gasping )
( groans )
Oh, nice time for a swim!
( gasping )
Either this is
a Destiny Stone,
or it's a giant matzah ball!
( screams )
Hold on!
( groaning )
( screams )
I hope you're satisfied.
Now you've ruined the soup
and the Destiny Stone!
( slurping )
( sighing )
Not bad for a bunch of kids.
It's a good thing
the chef left broth!
Maybe so, but we
added a special touch.
Yeah, everybody's hands
went in the soup.
Tastes better that way.
( laughing )
TK: There's something strange
about this soup, Cody.
Huh?
I have this weird feeling
that we'll figure out
how to DNA Digivolve.
Must be the MSG.
( laughing )
Huh?
Why'd it go dark?
That's the light
of a Destiny Stone!
( dramatic music )
A perfect turn of events.
How lucky!
Now the digital world
will be my oyster.
Now I need my black pearl.
Help, I've got a mushroom
on my nose, help!
( grunts )
Go get it!
( shouting )
The final Destiny Stone.
I hope you came for the soup.
I'll shatter it to pieces!
DAVIS: Stop!
Figures, those nosy kids
always show up
at the wrong time!
Don't try it
or we'll turn you into
a heap of sardine cans!
You just never seem
to learn your lesson, do you?
Obnoxious parasites.
Show 'em what you're made of,
BlackWarGreymon!
I don't need you to tell me.
( shouting )
Cody, I think the time
has come for us
‐ to put that big guy away.
‐ Yep!
I'm ready whenever
you are, Angemon!
I am too, let's let her rip!
Payback time!
Save some for me!
Digimon.
Exveemon!
Stingmon!
BOTH: DNA Digivolve to...
Paildramon!
♪ Digimon, digital monsters ♪
♪ Digimon ♪
Let's get him!
I'm with you.
Digimon.
Aquilamon!
Gatomon!
BOTH: DNA Digivolve to...
Silphymon!
Terra Destroyer!
( gasping )
Desperado Blaster!
Static Force!
( gasping )
Ready?
Yeah, let's go!
Give it all you've got!
Yeah!
Digimon.
Ankylomon!
Angemon!
BOTH: DNA Digivolve to...
Shakkoumon!
♪ Digimon ♪
BOTH: Wow, Shakkoumon!
We did it!
( laughing )
Whoa, way to go, guys!
Shakkoumon's
a totally awesome Digimon!
BlackWarGreymon is gonna have
a major challenge on his hands!
This is it, the final battle!
( dramatic music )
NARRATOR: Will Shakkoumon
be able to defeat
BlackWarGreymon?
Don't miss
the battle of the century
on Digimon: Digital Monsters!
♪