NARRATOR: Arukenimon and
Mummymon searched all over
for the legendary Destiny Stone.
Once they found it, Arukenimon
created Knightmon to destroy it
but our guy's DNA digivolved
and we were to stop him.
Meanwhile, Agumon
confronted BlackWarGreymon
and tried to convince
him to be his friend.
Yeah, good luck.
But just as BlackWarGreymon
was coming around, he got this
weird feeling and left
to find the Destiny Stone.
There was nothing we could do.
We had to watch
as BlackWarGreymon
destroyed the Destiny Stone.
Is this the end
of the Digital World?
("Digimon Are The Champions")
♪ Di Di Di Digimon
♪ Digimon
♪ Di Di Di
♪ Digimon, Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon are the champions
♪ Change into Digital Champions
♪ To save the Digital World
♪ Digimon, Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon are the champions
♪ Digivolve into champions
♪ Armor, digivolve
♪ Digimon, Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon are the champions
♪ Digimon
‐ Yay I'm finally in Kyoto!
CLASSMATE: Yolei, hurry
or you'll miss the bus!
‐ I'm coming!
Dear Poromon and Izzy,
how's it going guys?
This is the second
day of our school trip
and we're finally in Kyoto!
I'm having a great time with
my friends, what a cool place!
And the food is fab!
Poromon, if you're good
I'll bring you a souvenir.
Ciao for now, Yolei.
‐ According to everything
you've just told me, this whole
mess started when your
digivice changed into a D3.
If my calculations are
correct, it's all your fault!
‐ Huh?
‐ The other needed D3s in
order to compete with you,
so their sub‐conscious
minds must have
willed their
digivices to change,
although I'm not sure Davis
has a sub‐conscious mind.
As strong as these
digivices are,
they just weren't enough.
Of course, that also
means you must have made
a wish for your digivice
to change into a D3.
‐ I don't remember
making any wishes.
In fact, I always
got the short side
of the wishbone from the turkey.
‐ Like I said, it must've
been your sub‐conscious.
We geniuses have
pretty pig ones.
In the Digital World, data
is formed into shapes,
usually based on whatever
a person has running
through their mind, kinda
like a VCR for the brain.
And that's the reason why
everyone's clothes change
every time they go into the
Digital World, and why Davis
looks the way he does, like
a fighter pilot on safari.
‐ I see.
So, then I must have wished
for that Digimon Emperor outfit.
‐ So you're not perfect.
You should read Singbold's
Theory of Ultimate Brain Power.
You might be able
to pick up a few pointers.
‐ Actually, I taught
a class on it.
But don't you think Tsaro's
Strengthening Your Mind
was more effective?
‐ Uh, yeah.
But of course, Gorski's
My Brain My Buddy
is the quintessential
masterpiece when it comes to
exploring the inner
working of the human mind.
But I'm sure you've read it a
dozen times, it's a bestseller
in the school's psychology
department bookstore.
‐ I'm sorry, Izzy.
I can't believe I've
never heard of that one,
I feel so ashamed of myself.
‐ Oh, don't worry.
I've got another
copy you can borrow.
After all, we high‐IQ types
gotta stick together, right?
Besides, of all the other
digi‐destined I've met,
you're one of the only
ones as smart as me!
‐ Other digi‐destined?
What are you talking about, huh?
‐ Oh, I guess no one told you
we're not the only ones around.
Actually, there are quite
a few of us all over the world.
I haven't met them all,
but I'm working on it.
It seems that most of us
have one thing in common,
we all had some kind
of encounter with the digimon
when they invaded the real
world a few years ago.
And now we each have
our own digimon partner.
‐ I see, that means
that I must've, too.
Everything from that time
is still such a blur to me.
‐ Oh, Poromon,
there's an e‐mail here
for you from Yolei on her trip.
‐ Hey, what's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
‐ Oh, he's just really tired
because he's been
here in the real world
for a couple
of days without Yolei.
I know sometimes
when Ken's not here
even my naps make me exhausted.
‐ Yolei asked me to watch
him while she was on
her school trip, and it's been
three days since she left.
I've noticed that,
as each day passes, he seems
to get more and more tired,
and he's not very hungry.
You know it's really
gotta bad when he'd
rather sleep than eat a bag
of chocolate gummy chews.
‐ Well then I'll just
have to take him into
the Digital World so that
he can regain his strength.
Davis and the
others have already
gone on ahead, haven't they?
‐ Yeah, you're right,
that's a great idea Ken.
Here you go.
Things are kinda
crazy there now,
so be careful of any warps.
Promise me you won't talk
to any strange digimon.
‐ I'll be fine.
Hey, Izzy, d'you think
I can ever make up
for all the trouble I've caused?
‐ Look, Ken, we
all make mistakes.
When we first went
to the Digital World,
I came up with
a bunch of theories.
Not all of them
were exactly right.
But I was only a kid then.
I eventually realized
that you have to have
all the facts before
hypothesizing.
We need to learn all we can
about the Digital World.
I know that somewhere
down the road,
we'll be called on again
to help the Digital World.
Let's just make
sure that this time
we're both totally prepared.
TEACHER: Alright, listen up.
I want you all to meet
back here in two hours.
STUDENTS: Okay.
‐ I told my whole family I
would bring them back souvenirs.
‐ There!
‐ That was fast!
‐ Okay, now we can
see the sights.
Huh, tell me I'm not seeing
what I think I'm seeing!
( terrified scream )
BLACKWARGREYMON:
Terra Destroyer!
I'll demolish them all,
and once I do,
my suffering will
finally come to an end!
‐ Yeah, whatever.
Stop the talking
and keep destroying!
I've got a deadline
to meet, I haven't got all day!
‐ I'm so proud of that boy,
sometimes it just
makes me want to cry.
BLACKWARGREYMON:
Terra Destroyer!
‐ Rats, we got here to late!
‐ What's that?
‐ It's warping!
‐ The area is starting
to become unbalanced!
I saw a warp when he destroyed
the other one too,
but it was smaller then.
It seems that every time
BlackWarGreymon destroys one
of those stones, the warp
just gets bigger and bigger!
‐ Hey, look what's
happening to him now!
‐ What?
‐ Oh.
I was right,
it's BlackWarGreymon!
( menacing growling )
‐ Ahh, why is everybody standing
around like nothing's happening?
What's wrong with you people?
( crowd murmuring )
( growling )
( panting )
Wait!
( growling )
‐ Stop, you, er, digimon!
‐ Huh?
‐ ( scared cry )
‐ ( digimon grunting )
APEMON: I am Apemon,
I swing into action
and use my Mega Bone Stick
attack to demolish my enemies!
‐ I've got to tell the
others what's going on!
Emergency, Digimon
are now in Kyoto!
Hurry, having
a wonderful time, Yolei.
( evil laugh )
ARUKENIMON: When will
you children ever learn,
you can't possibly beat me!
‐ Ha, we'll see about
that, let's go, Veemon!
EXVEEMON: Veemon,
digivolve to ExVeemon!
ANKYLOMON: Armadillomon,
digivolve to Ankylomon!
PEGASUSMON: Patamon,
armor digivolve to...
Pegasusmon, flying hope!
NEFERTIMON: Gatomon,
armor digivolve to...
Nefertimon, the angel of light!
‐ That's just a legend.
‐ I'm not so sure.
‐ Huh, wait a minute,
what was that?
‐ What do you mean,
it was a rehearsal!
‐ That's not what I mean.
I just saw something.
‐ Ahh! Get my agent!
‐ Oh, good, there he is.
Of course now what
am I supposed to do?
‐ Uhh, good dog?
‐ There it is, alright,
Stingmon, do your thing!
STINGMON: Right!
( growls )
‐ Stingmon!
‐ Yolei!
‐ Ken, I don't get it.
‐ I'll explain
everything to you later.
Stingmon, remember, he's
not a Control Spire digimon
so you can't destroy him!
STINGMON: Don't worry, Ken!
( grunting )
Ken, I got him
‐ Alright, Yolei,
the rest is up to you now!
‐ What are you talking about?
Come back!
POROMON: Okay, Yolei,
I'm ready for action!
What shall we do first?
‐ Hey, I thought
I left you with Izzy.
What are you doing here?
‐ It's a long story.
‐ I found her,
she's over here, professor!
Excuse me, miss,
are you the girl
who called out digimon before?
YOLEI: Uhh, maybe?
‐ I have one more
question to ask.
YOLEI: What is it?
‐ That's a digimon
you're holding, isn't it?
‐ Oh boy.
Who are you guys?
‐ Oh, I'm sorry,
I'm Professor Takenouchi.
I teach folklore at the
university in Tokyo,
but I've been spending the
last year doing research
right here in the city of Kyoto.
And this is‐‐
‐ My name's Jim, Joe's brother.
I'm one of the
professor's students.
I was pre‐med and had
to study everything
from brain surgery to bedpans.
And then I took one class
with the professor here.
I changed my major
to ghosts and goblins,
my kid brother still wants
to be a doctor, though.
‐ How nice.
I'm Yolei Inoue
and I'm in eighth grade.
I live in Tokyo too.
But I'm not too sure
what I'm doing here.
JIM: I knew it!
My little brother
told me all about you!
‐ Huh?
‐ Yep, and I've heard
a lot of good things
about you from my
daughter as well.
‐ And, uh, I guess that means
that you're referring
to Joe Kido and Sora Takenouchi?
‐ Bullseye!
‐ Huh?
EXVEEMON: Vee Laser!
‐ And now it's my turn!
‐ ExVeemon!
‐ Davis! You alright?
‐ Where were you?
I've been waiting,
are you ready?
‐ Let's do it!
EXVEEMON: ExVeemon!
STINGMON: Stingmon!
♪ Champions
EXVEEMON AND STINGMON:
DNA Digivolve to...
PAILDRAMON: Paildramon!
‐ I've studied legends
all over the world.
The Loch Ness Monster,
Bigfoot, the Bermuda Triangle.
You should see my
Frequent Flyer Miles.
Anyway, I don't spend
much time at home.
I guess that's what caused
Sora to be so angry.
Then three years ago,
she suddenly
turned into a whole new person.
She and her mother
became best friends,
I thought maybe she had
a boyfriend or was going through
one of those teenage things,
but she simply said
that she owed it all
to her friends, the digimon.
‐ Her friends the digimon?
‐ That's right, her adventures
with them forced her
to grow up and change her
outlook on everything.
Especially the stormy
relationship with her mother.
You should see them now,
shopping every Saturday,
my credit card's at the limit!
‐ Oh.
‐ So thanks to the digimon,
our family is a lot closer now,
even though
I'm still never around.
‐ You're welcome!
‐ That's a beautiful story.
Thanks for sharing.
‐ I'm glad I'm getting to see
a digimon on a friendly basis.
I've had a run‐in with
them before, you know.
When everything happened
three years ago,
I was right in the
middle of the battle.
Actually, my brother Joe
was a little more involved.
I was sorta helping
from the sidelines.
It's not that I couldn't have
helped him fight, it's just
that I wanted to give the kid
a chance to learn on his own.
‐ I still don't get it.
Of all the cities
they could've picked,
why did the digimon start
showing up here in Kyoto?
‐ Ever since Kyoto
became the capital,
residents here feel
the city has developed
a very strong connection
with animal spirits.
‐ What?
‐ That's right, different
animals like raccoons and foxes.
One of the reasons
I'm here is to determine
if these stories
are based on fact.
Another reason is
there's an outlet mall
where I can get my
socks for half price.
‐ I see.
PROFESSOR: Kyoto was chosen
to be the capital partly
because the four gods are in
harmony surrounding the city.
Have you heard that story?
‐ I'm not sure.
PROFESSOR: It's
quite interesting.
You see, the mountains
to the north are for
Genbu the turtle, the river
to the east is for
Seiryuu the dragon,
the river to the south
is for Suzaku the phoenix,
and the road to the west
is for Byakko the tiger.
So the city was protected
by the mountains,
had the convenience of
a river and roads nearby,
and was open to the west.
A perfect scenario.
‐ Cool.
‐ There's also the Spirit Gate,
and the fact that
there were many temples
built in all four directions.
They believe that
without those temples,
it'd be too easy for the
magical creatures to get in.
‐ Spirits?
Creatures?
‐ Professor!
‐ Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Sometimes I get wrapped
up in my own stories.
The city has changed
a lot since those days.
What I'm trying to say is
that Kyoto is close to the
spirit world, in other words,
any world other than our own.
‐ Like the Digital World?
‐ I have a theory that those
digimon you saw running around
found it easier to travel
through the warp in the
Digital World to Kyoto rather
than trying to go to Tokyo.
‐ Wait a minute, are you
trying to tell me that digimon
are some sort of
magical creatures?
‐ Well aren't they?
‐ Huh?
‐ It's not like they're
just a collection of data.
I believe that digimon are
actually legends that people
have spoken of for hundreds
of years, and, over time,
have gained a level
of consciousness
and become a reality.
I think that digimon
may have started
as data in some old computer,
but have since come alive.
Just like those old legends.
Do you agree with my theory?
‐ Uh, huh?
( surprised cry )
Hey stop the car,
there they are!
MONSTER: Huh?
‐ Ah, what's that?
( growls )
POROMON: That's
Musyamon, a warrior digimon
who can take different shapes.
I've seen him use his
Shogun Sword attack
to make mincemeat
out of his enemies!
Should I?
‐ Go for it.
POROMON: Poromon,
digivolve to Hawkmon!
‐ You can do it, Hawkmon!
‐ Do you think Hawkmon
would let me interview him?
‐ Feather Strike!
‐ Hawkmon, armor Digivolve!
‐ Glad to.
‐ Digi ever energize!
♪ Digimon
HAWKMON: Hawkmon,
armor digivolve to...
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
♪ Digimon are the champions
NARRATOR: Armor, digivolve.
♪ Digimon, digital monsters
SHURIMON: Shurimon,
the samurai of sincerity!
Double Star!
‐ Professor, do
you suggest I start
taking notes about
what I'm seeing?
‐ Never mind the notes,
drive the car!
‐ Right!
♪ It's getting stranger and then
♪ It's getting harder to win
‐ Professor, do you happen
to have a laptop computer?
‐ Um, yeah.
‐ Shogun Sword!
‐ Double Star!
♪ Hey
♪ It doesn't really
matter who you are
♪ You might as well
be a super star
♪ 'Cause everything has
gone way too far, oh oh oh
‐ Digiport, open!
Shurimon, the port is open!
( Musyamon screams )
Jim! Close it!
‐ He's vanished.
‐ No, Jim, he didn't vanish.
He returned to the
Digital World where he belongs.
( sigh of relief )
‐ You did a good job.
But we have to figure out a
way to stop BlackWarGreymon.
Look, Yolei,
something happening to them!
JIM: They're all returning
to the Digital World.
‐ Yeah, but I've got a question.
Why did they come here
to the real world?
I don't get it.
‐ It may not make sense to us,
but there must
have been a reason.
YOLEI VOICEOVER: That was
really strange.
I was able to open the
digiport and send Musyamon
back to the Digital
World, but Tai
and the others
weren't able to do it.
‐ Yolei!
‐ Huh?
We'd better hurry up and
get you back to your class.
After all, you
don't want to miss
the rest of your
school trip, do you?
‐ Oh, I almost
forgot about that!
‐ Huh?
They have returned,
Mummymon, let's go!
MUMMYMON: Right!
DAVIS: Going somewhere?
‐ I don't have time for small
talk with small children.
I wouldn't get too
comfortable if I were you,
there are still five more
Destiny Stones out there,
and when I destroy them,
there goes the Digital World!
‐ Is she serious?
‐ She won't stop until she
finds all the Destiny Stones.
‐ And if she destroys them all.
‐ Then the balance
of the Digital World
will be destroyed as well.
KEN VOICEOVER: Now I
finally understand,
this must be what Izzy
was worried about.
If the balance of the
Digital World is destroyed,
something terrible
is going to happen.
‐ Nice meeting you, Yolei.
And be sure to say
hi to Sora for me
when you get back to Tokyo.
‐ And to Joe too.
‐ Sure, nice meeting you!
‐ Yolei, where have you been?
‐ I had to take care of
a couple of small things.
‐ Hey, look what's that?
‐ Ah just a souvenir,
a very quiet souvenir.
‐ Ah, it's so cute!
( distraught yelling )
Ugh, sorry about that, Poromon.
NARRATOR: What are the
mysterious Destiny Stones?
Will Arukenimon be able
to destroy them all?
Find out next time on
Digimon: Digital Monsters!
( children laughing )
( "Digimon Are The Champions" )