Yolei: WE FOUND
THIS GREAT RESTAURANT,
BUT DIDN'T HAVE
ANY DIGIDOLLARS.
MIMI'S GORGEOUS FRIEND MICHAEL
OFFERED TO PAY THE CHECK.
T.K. REMEMBERED
THAT DIGITAMAMON WAS EVIL,
BUT HE SWORE HE CHANGED.
I DIDN'T BELIEVE IT
FOR A SECOND.
HE PROVED I WAS RIGHT
WHEN HE ATTACKED MIMI.
THE DIGIEGG OF SINCERITY
FOUND ME,
AND HAWKMON DIGEVOLVED
INTO SHURIMON
WHO DESTROYED
DIGITAMAMON'S DARK SPIRAL.
I'M GLAD TO HAVE
A SECOND DIGIEGG,
BUT I'M MORE EXCITED
TO SEE MICHAEL AGAIN.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
THOSE KIDS CAN FORGET
THIS AREA.
IT'S ALL YOURS, BOSS.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
Veemon: HA HA HA HA!
Davis: VEEMON, HOLD STILL.
I STILL HAVE TO CLEAN
THE DIRT OFF YOUR TOENAILS.
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING,
TAP-DANCING IN A FRYING PAN?
QUIT WIGGLING AROUND
SO MUCH.
I CAN'T STOP.
IT TICKLES.
LET ME WASH UNDER YOUR ARMS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO STINK.
CAN I JUST BE STINKY?
ALL MY GIRLFRIENDS WILL THINK
THAT STINK'S COMING FROM ME.
TICKLE, TICKLE,
TICKLE!
NO FAIR! I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE WASHING YOU!
I'M GOING TO BUST A GUT
IN A MINUTE!
Both: HA HA HA!
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
IT COULD BE
JUST MY IMAGINATION,
BUT EVERYBODY IN MY FAMILY
HAS GONE NUTS.
Man: AND NOW
FOR A NEWS UPDATE --
KENNETH ICHIJOUJI,
THE BOY GENIUS,
REPORTED MISSING
FOR THE PAST TWO MONTHS,
HAS STILL NOT BEEN FOUND.
POLICE BELIEVE HE PLOTTED
HIS OWN DISAPPEARANCE,
EVEN THOUGH THEY HAVE NOT HAD
ANY SOLID LEADS SO FAR.
HYAH!
HUH?
DAD! I WAS WATCHING THAT!
DADS HAVE DIBS
ON THE REMOTE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
IT'S YOUR BEDTIME.
[ GRUMBLES ]
PICK UP YOUR TOYS.
I ALMOST FELL ON MY BUTT.
LOOKS LIKE MY SPACE
HAS BEEN INVADED.
MY BROTHER IS GETTING
ON MY NERVES.
LET'S GO TO THE DIGIWORLD
TOMORROW.
YOLEI'S BROTHER
NEEDS US.
HA HA HA.
MAKE SURE YOU ALL
GET SLEEP.
YOU'LL NEED IT TO FIGHT
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
HMM.
BETTER SNOOZE...
Veemon: OR WE'LL LOSE!
LISTEN UP!
WE GOT BIG TROUBLE,
AND IT'S REALLY A DOOZY!
SHOGUN GEKOMON!
OH, HE'S PROBABLY WEARING
THOSE EARPLUGS AGAIN.
SHOGUN GEKOMON,
WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY!
AAH! WAKE UP!
THIS IS NO TIME TO ZONE OUT!
IT'S A TOTAL DISASTER!
DIGIMON EMPEROR HAS PUT UP
A CONTROL SPIRE!
WHAT? NO WAY!
HOLD ON! COULD YOU WAIT
TILL I GET OFF THIS THING?
I'M AFRAID OF HEIGHTS!
GADZOOKS!
THIS IS HORRIBLE!
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S GOT
HIS HOT LITTLE MITTS
ON OUR TERRITORY!
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING,
OR WE'RE GOING TO BE SLAVES
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES!
FACING HIM IS LIKE A PICCOLO
GOING UP AGAINST A TUBA!
OH, I'M TOO TIRED
FOR THIS!
[ SCREAMING AND YELLING ]
Yolei: DAVIS,
LET'S GET MOVING!
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR HAS REALLY
STARTED TO MOVE FASTER!
HE'S NOT AFRAID OF US,
OR HE WOULDN'T KEEP FIGHTING
AFTER LOSING ALL THOSE BATTLES.
Yolei: LOOK!
WE BETTER TAKE THE SPIN
OUT OF HIS WHEELS AND FAST!
I'M NOT GOING
TO LET THAT BRAINIAC
GET THE BEST OF US!
HE'S PLOTTING
SOMETHING BIG.
IF I WERE AN EVIL GENIUS,
WHAT WOULD I DO?
WE'VE GOT TO TAKE ONE OF
THOSE AREAS BACK FROM HIM.
All: MM-HMM!
WE'RE GOING TO TEACH
THAT DIGIMON EMPEROR A LESSON
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
Gatomon: [ Coughs ] THE DUST
IS MAKING MY WHISKERS TWITCH.
Armadillomon: THIS PLACE
IS WEIRD.
NOT TO MENTION OLD.
IT'S REMINISCENT OF
THE SAMURAI ERA IN JAPAN.
IT COULD BE A FILM SET
FROM AN OLD TV SHOW.
I THINK THIS IS DEFINITELY
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
SEE THAT?
T.K.: IT'S A CONTROL SPIRE.
THAT'S A SURE SIGN.
WHAT WAS THAT?
Yolei: YEAH, RED EYES
GIVE ME THE CREEPS.
THIS LOOKS BAD.
WHAT ARE THEY WAITING FOR?
THEY ALREADY HAVE US SURROUNDED.
[ YELLING ]
ME AND MY BIG MOUTH.
WE'RE FLORAMON!
WE MAY LOOK LIKE FLOWERS,
BUT WATCH OUT!
OUR RAIN OF POLLEN
WILL MAKE HAY FEVER
SEEM LIKE A WALK IN THE ROSES.
WE'RE MUSHROOMON.
YOU DEFINITELY DON'T WANT US
IN YOUR VEGGIE OMELET.
WE MAY BE CUTE AS BUTTONS,
BUT OUR FUNGUS CRUNCHER
WILL LEAVE YOU
SCRATCHING YOUR HEAD.
All: RAIN OF POLLEN
COMING AT YOU!
FUNGUS...
CRUNCHER! CRUNCHER!
STAND BACK!
BOULDER COMING THROUGH!
YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR ME,
GATOMON!
OH, YEAH?
CAT'S EYE HYPNOTISM!
I'M TOO TIRED
TO PLAY ANYMORE.
I THINK
I'LL TAKE A NAPPY NOW.
FUNGUS CRUNCHER!
HAWK BEAM!
I'M NOT GETTING FRIED!
I'VE HAD IT!
HMM? AAH!
WHO DID THAT?
Hawkmon: I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
THAT STAR BELONGS TO NINJAMON.
HE'LL ATTACK AT THE MOST
INAPPROPRIATE MOMENT.
HE'S A VERY VULGAR DIGIMON,
IF YOU ASK ME.
HA! SO I MANAGED
TO MISS YOU THIS TIME.
SO WHAT?
I WAS JUST PRACTICING.
BUT NEXT TIME, I'M GOING
TO SPLIT SOME FEATHERS.
Yolei: IF YOU THINK YOU'RE
THE TOP NINJA, THINK AGAIN.
I'M SORRY TO TELL YOU,
BUT YOU'RE NUMBER TWO
ON THE FOOD CHAIN.
COME ON! WHAT BIRDBRAIN
CALLS HIMSELF NUMBER ONE?
I'M AFRAID
THAT HAS TO BE ME.
TRY HIM AND SEE.
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
HAWKMON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
SHURIMON,
THE SAMURAI OF SINCERITY.
THAT'S A PRETTY FANCY MOVE,
BUT I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU.
WANT TO SEE MORE?
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE,
BIG SHOT?
HYAH!
GO, SHURIMON!
YOU'RE BETTER
THAN THE MOVIE!
HUH?
FUNGUS CRUNCHER!
RAIN OF POLLEN!
AAH!
[ YELLING ]
V-HEAD BUTT!
DIAMOND SHELL!
BOOM BUBBLE!
LIGHTNING PAW!
THEY'RE UNDER HIS SPELL!
THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM,
HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY
FREE THEM ALL?
YOU GUYS, THESE FUNGAZOIDS
WON'T GIVE ME A BREAK!
[ YELLING ]
COME ON!
YOU CAN HIDE DOWN HERE.
HUH? GEKOMON?
HURRY UP
BEFORE THEY FIND YOU!
WE CAN ESCAPE
DOWN BELOW!
A MANHOLE COVER --
I WASN'T UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT THEY HAD THOSE THINGS
IN ANCIENT JAPAN.
YOU'VE GOT TO REALIZE THAT
THIS IS THE DIGITAL WORLD.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN HERE.
WHO CARES? QUIT TALKING
AND HUSTLE DOWN, OKAY?
WIND IT UP, SHURIMON!
WE'VE GOT TO MOVE!
PLEASE! WE'VE GOT
A SCHEDULE TO KEEP.
STOP FIGHTING
AND COME ON!
SORRY, BUT DUTY CALLS,
AND SO DOES YOLEI.
WE'LL SEE EACH OTHER
AGAIN.
Shogun: ON BEHALF
OF THE GEKOMON,
WE THANK YOU FROM THE BOTTOM
OF OUR HORNS.
IF YOU HADN'T SHOWN UP,
WE'D STILL BE SERVANTS
OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
WE APPRECIATE WHAT YOU DID
FOR US. YOU SAVED OUR LIVES.
YEAH.
YOU GUYS ARE A LOT NICER
THAN LAST TIME I SAW YOU.
YOU SURE WERE EVIL,
NOT THAT I'M BLAMING YOU.
I'D BE PRETTY MEAN, TOO,
IF I HAD A DARK RING AROUND ME.
BUT THAT'S OVER,
AND WE'RE FRIENDS.
IS THIS WHERE YOU
ARE LIVING --
BENEATH THE GROUND?
I'M AFRAID IT'S THE ONLY
SAFE PLACE TO BE.
CAN YOU GUYS GIVE US
THE INSIDE SCOOP
ON WHERE THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
IS HIDING THESE DAYS?
HE'S BEEN INCOGNITO.
THE DARK RINGS
JUST FLEW RIGHT IN HERE
AND BRAINWASHED EVERYONE
IN SIGHT.
THAT MEANS THE DIGIMON
EMPEROR KNOWS WHERE YOU ARE,
AND HE CAN
FIND YOU AGAIN.
WE DON'T WANT TO BE THE DIGIMON
EMPEROR'S SLAVES AGAIN.
THAT WAS WAY TOO AWFUL.
SHOGUN GEKOMON,
DO YOU HAVE ANY GOOD IDEAS?
YES, WE DO.
THAT'S SIMPLE,
MY LITTLE FRIEND.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
[ GRUNTING ]
WELL...
WE SLEEP.
Gatomon: [ Sarcastically ]
OH, SURE, THAT'LL HELP.
Ninjamon: HEH HEH HEH!
[ SNORING ]
I'M SORRY, BUT SNOOZING
ON THE JOB IS COUNTERPRODUCTIVE.
[ GROANING ]
GRRAAH!
HE'S YOURS, MASTER.
FIRST, WE HAVE TO DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE.
THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
DON'T YOU THINK SO,
VEEMON?
BESIDES, WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT BIG MUSCLE DIGIMON.
MOST OF THEM WOULD RATHER
TOSS A SALAD INSTEAD.
HA HA HA HA.
WHOA!
[ GASPS ]
IT'S AN EARTHQUAKE!
I HATE EARTHQUAKES.
AND MY BROTHER
WAKING ME EVERY MORNING.
DON'T WORRY, YOLEI.
YOU CAN RELAX.
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
THE SHOGUN'S COME UNGLUED!
HE'S TEARING THE PLACE APART!
WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO!
GEKO! GEKO!
GEKO!
HMM?
ON, NO, LOOK!
HE'S GOT A DARK SPIRAL!
I'VE SEEN HIM
IN ACTION BEFORE.
SHOGUN GEKOMON
IS AN ULTIMATE DIGIMON.
YOU MAY THINK
HE JUST TOOTS HIS HORN,
BUT HE CAN PLAY A NOTE
SO FLAT,
IT'LL FLATTEN EVERYTHING
AROUND HIM.
GEKOMON, EVACUATE
BEFORE YOU GET STEPPED ON!
GRRAAH!
SOMEONE HELP!
QUICK! I'M STUCK!
I CAN'T GET OUT
OF HERE!
I'VE GOT YOU.
IF THE SHOGUN'S
BEING CONTROLLED
BY THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
HE'S BIG AND OBNOXIOUS,
BUT WE LIKE HIM.
CAN YOU DO SOMETHING?
HUH? OF COURSE.
JUST LEAVE IT TO US.
T.K., STEP IT UP. THEY'VE
GOT US ALL SURROUNDED.
Gekomon: [ CRYING ]
COME ON, VEEMON,
LET'S PLANT THESE GUYS.
I'M WITH YOU!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
VEEMON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
RAGEDRAMON --
THE STORM OF FRIENDSHIP!
GRRAAH!
TAKE HIM DOWN,
PATAMON!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
PATAMON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
PEGASUSMON -- FLYING HOPE!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
GATOMON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
NEFERTIMON --
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER!
LET'S JOIN THE TROOPS,
HAWKMON!
OF COURSE.
THERE'S A NOTE ON THE STAR.
"FROM NINJAMON."
WHAT DOES IT SAY?
HE WANTS
TO CHALLENGE ME.
HMM...
WHAT KIND OF CHALLENGE?
EQUUS BEAM!
CAT'S EYE BEAM!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S NOT WORKING!
Kari: HE DIDN'T
EVEN YAWN.
WHOA!
JUST MELLOW OUT, GUYS.
NEED A LIFT?
YEAH, I HAVE
ENOUGH VEGETABLES.
LAUGHING SMASHER!
THUNDER BLAST!
THEY'RE COMING!
I'LL PUT THEM IN THE GARDEN
WHERE THEY BELONG.
ROCK CRACKING!
AAH!
Yolei: WHAT DO YOU THINK
HE'S DOING UP HERE?
Shurimon: MEDITITING?
[ Sarcastically ]
YEAH, RIGHT.
WAKE UP!
I ACCEPT
YOUR DANCE INVITATION.
GOOD.
THEN LET'S BOOGIE.
COME ON! KNOCK THAT
LITTLE TWERP'S SOCKS OFF!
AAH! MISSED ME!
HUH? AAH!
HEY, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO WIN THIS!
GRRAAH!
MUSICAL FIST!
[ GASPS ]
Pegasusmon:
THAT WAS CLOSE!
THERE'S NO WAY WE'LL BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT AN ULTIMATE
ON OUR OWN.
[ Thinking ] SOMEHOW,
WE'VE GOT TO GET HIM
TO DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE.
LET'S MOVE INTO POSITION!
IT'S PERFECT, T.K.
MUSICAL FIST!
IT'S COMING!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
WOW! CHECK IT OUT!
[ GROANING ]
SUDDENLY, I FEEL
LIKE MYSELF AGAIN.
I'M SORRY,
BUT THIS IS YOUR STOP.
WATCH THAT FIRST STEP.
WELL, HE'S ALL YOURS NOW,
DAVIS.
GOTCHA, T.I.
THUNDER BLAST!
GEKO! GEKO!
YOU KNOW THE DRILL,
DIGMON.
I'LL MAKE HIM EAT DIRT!
GOLD RUSH!
GEKO!
[ GROANS ]
YOU DID IT!
HEY, WHERE'S YOLEI?
HAWKMON'S MISSING, TOO.
IT FIGURES. SHE'S ALWAYS
UP TO SOMETHING.
THE CONTROL SPIRE'S
BEEN DESTROYED.
FIGHT TIME IS OVER NOW!
SORRY, YOLEI,
THIS IS BETWEEN GENTLEMEN.
LET ME INTRODUCE YOU
TO A FEW OF MY FRIENDS.
HUH?
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF MULTIPLICATION?
NINJA WIND!
WHERE'D HE GO?
I PREFER SUBTRACTION.
DOUBLE STARS!
WHO'S NUMBER ONE?
[ SIGHS ]
DON'T BE A POOR SPORT.
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
I'M GOING TO TURN YOU
INTO A DISHRAG.
TILL THEN, PAL!
SHURIMON, HAVE I
EVER TOLD YOU
YOU'RE THE COOLEST GUY
I'VE EVER MET?
HUH? OH, YOLEI...
[ SNORING ]
Kari: GEE, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE BIG GUY'S ALL CRASHED OUT.
Geko: [ Sarcastically ]
THAT'S RARE.
HA HA!
YOU'RE BACK, YOLEI!
WE WERE WORRIED.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
JUST HERE AND THERE.
WE'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU COULD TAKE
THE DARK SPIRAL OFF HIS HEAD.
HOW ABOUT WE CHOP IT ALL OFF?
HE NEEDS A HAIRCUT.
WHAT? YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
THAT'S HIS PRIDE AND JOY!
WITHOUT HIS TOPKNOT,
HE'LL BE BALD!
IF YOU THINK
HE WAS MAD BEFORE,
JUST TRY CATCHING HIM
ON A BAD HAIR DAY!
DAVIS, SOMETIMES
YOU'RE SO INSENSITIVE.
I'M SO SENSITIVE
I USE A SPECIAL TOOTHPASTE
SO MY TEETH DON'T HURT
WHEN I EAT ICE CREAM!
HA HA HA HA!
T.K.: ZAP THAT SPIRAL
WITH ALL WE'VE GOT!
EQUUS BEAM!
CAT'S EYE BEAM!
THUNDER BLAST!
GOLD RUSH!
DOUBLE STARS!
[ CRYING ]
HUH?
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
THAT WAS A GREAT SIESTA.
ANYTHING GOOD HAPPEN
WHILE I WAS OUT?
[ CRYING ]
Geko: WE'RE JUST SO GLAD
YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL AGAIN.
OF COURSE I AM.
I JUST HAD A NAP.
BY THE WAY, I REALLY LIKE
YOUR HAIRCUT.
TALK ABOUT CHANGING
YOUR MIND ALL THE TIME.
Cody: HEY, DAVIS, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD GET A NEW HAIRSTYLE.
Kari: HOW ABOUT
A TOPKNOT?
THE DIGIDESTINED HAVE
DEFEATED YOU AGAIN, MASTER.
WELL, PERHAPS THEY THINK
THEY HAVE, ANYWAY.
THOSE HALF-WITS HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THEY'RE UP AGAINST.
I'M JUST PUTTING THEM
IN POSITION.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'LL
FIGURE OUT MY MASTER PLAN
BECAUSE I'M JUST
WAY TOO SMART FOR THEM.
Man: WHAT IS THE DIGIMON
EMPEROR'S MASTER PLAN?
PERHAPS HE'LL REVEAL IT
ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."