Davis: THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
TRIED TO KEEP US DIGIDESTINED
FROM DESTROYING ANY MORE
OF HIS CONTROL SPIRES
BY SICCING ANDROMON ON US.
KARI RECOGNIZED HIM RIGHT AWAY
AS HER OLD FRIEND.
I WASN'T SO SURE
'CAUSE THIS ANDROMON
ONLY RESPONDED
TO THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
LUCKILY,
THE EMPEROR'S DARK RINGS
COULDN'T COMPLETELY
CONTROL HIM.
OUR D-3's WERE ABLE
TO FREE OUR BUDDY
FROM THE EMPEROR'S CONTROL.
THOUGH THAT BATTLE WAS WON,
THE WAR WAS FAR FROM OVER.
IF WE ONLY KNEW
WHO THIS EMPEROR GUY IS,
MAYBE WE COULD GUESS
HIS GAME PLAN
AND FIGURE OUT
HOW TO STOP HIM.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Boy: I GOT IT!
Boy #2: COME ON,
KICK IT!
Boy #3: SHOOT IT!
NO!
WHOA!
YOU WALK MUCH, DAVIS?
HA HA. HA HA.
ALL RIGHT, TEAM.
HUSTLE IN. LET'S GO.
NOW QUIET DOWN. I'VE GOT
AN ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE.
ALL RIGHT. OUR FIRST SCRIMMAGE
IS THIS SUNDAY.
IT'S AGAINST LAST YEAR'S
NUMBER ONE TEAM IN THE LEAGUE.
THAT'S THE TEAM
WITH THAT BRAINIAC KID.
HE'S GOOD AT SOCCER, SPORTS.
HE'S GOOD AT EVERYTHING.
HEY, HEY,
WATCH THE NAME-CALLING.
HE'S KEN ICHIJOUJI.
Yolei: "AS CAPTAIN
OF HIS SOCCER TEAM,
"KEN ICHIJOUJI LED HIS TEAM
TO VICTORY LAST SEASON
BY SCORING A RECORD-SETTING
45 GOALS."
Tai: THIS KID MAY EVEN BE
BETTER THAN I AM.
Cody: I BET HE COULD BE
IN THE OLYMPICS.
I NEVER EVEN GOT A CHANCE
TO BEAT HIM.
WE NEVER PLAYED HIS TEAM
LAST SEASON.
T.K.: YOU GUYS
GOT KNOCKED OUT EARLY.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN MAKE
THE PLAYOFFS.
Kari: YOU THINK
YOU CAN BEAT HIM?
I DON'T HAVE TO
FLAT OUT BEAT HIM.
IF I CAN MAKE IT A CLOSE GAME,
I'D BE A LIVING LEGEND,
AND EVERYONE KNOWS HOW MUCH
CHICKS DIG LIVING LEGENDS.
Yolei: OH, DAVIS.
UH-OH. IT'S HAPPENING
ALREADY.
WHEN YOU SEE KEN, WILL YOU
GET HIS AUTOGRAPH FOR ME?
Cody: YOLEI AND KEN
SITTING IN A TREE,
K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
I DIDN'T SAY
I WANTED TO KISS HIM.
I JUST WANT TO MARRY HIM.
ASK FOR HIS AUTOGRAPH
YOURSELF.
OH, I GUESS
I COULD DO THAT.
LET'S ALL GO TO THE GAME.
YOU CAN ASK HIM THEN.
HEY, DON'T YOU WANT
MY AUTOGRAPH?
CAN I COME
TO YOUR GAME, TOO, DAVIS?
SURE. YOU CAN WATCH ME
WIPE THE FIELD
WITH MR. PERFECT.
I'LL SHOW THEM
WHO'S THE MAN.
Woman: DID YOU SEE THAT?
Man: YEAH, IT'S GOING TO BE
A GOOD ONE.
[ GRUNTING AND GROANING ]
GOOD LUCK, DAVIS!
DON'T FORGET
TO HUG KEN!
GIVE HIM A KISS, TOO!
HA HA.
[ SCREAMING ]
ENJOY THE ATTENTION
WHILE IT LASTS, PAL.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S REALLY HIM.
[ Thinking ] WHEN I WOKE UP,
I WAS JUST A REGULAR KID.
WHEN I GO TO BED TONIGHT,
I'LL BE KING OF THE WORLD.
Tai: I HOPE DAVIS HASN'T
GOTTEN IN OVER HIS HEAD.
TAI PROBABLY THINKS
I'VE GOTTEN IN OVER MY HEAD.
WHERE'S KEN?
Kari: WHERE IS HE?
IZZY? NO, WE'RE WAITING
FOR KEN.
KEN'S NOT COMING,
IS HE, CODY?
WILL YOU STOP ASKING ME
IF I SAY YES?
OHH, LUCKY FOR ME,
I HAVE NO SPINE.
HELLO. UH, EXCUSE ME.
ANY OF YOU KNOW WHEN KEN
IS GOING TO BE HERE?
HE'S GOT A COMMERCIAL
TO SHOOT AND A MEETING
ABOUT HAVING A SOCCER BALL
NAMED AFTER HIM.
KEN HARDLY HAS TIME
TO PLAY ANYMORE.
I NEVER GET TO PLAY HIM.
HEY, DAVIS, CAN WE TALK?
EVEN IF KEN DOESN'T SHOW,
HIS TEAMMATES ARE CHAMPIONS.
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL,
THEY'LL USE YOU
AS THE BALL.
T.K.: IF YOU PLAY REALLY WELL
AGAINST LAST YEAR'S
CHAMPIONS...
Kari: WIN OR LOSE,
YOU'LL STILL BE A HERO.
YEAH, I'LL STILL BE
A LIVING LEGEND.
COOL!
WHY STAY
IF KEN ISN'T HERE?
IT'S NOT LIKE I DON'T HAVE
THINGS I COULD BE DOING.
WHAT ABOUT DAVIS?
♪ LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
[ Thinking ] I'VE GOT TO PLAY
AS WELL AS KEN. I'VE GOT TO.
♪ THAT WE CAN DO,
LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
♪ TOGETHER ♪
♪ NA-NA-NA-NA,
NA-NA-NA-NA ♪
♪ NA-NA-NA-NA ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THEY AIN'T
SEEN THE LAST ♪
♪ OF ME AND YOU ♪
♪ LET'S KICK IT UP ♪
♪ TOGETHER ♪
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
Kari: IT'S REWINDING. THERE.
YOU LOOK GOOD ON CAMERA.
Davis: THANKS, KARI.
I SO KICKED BUTT
OUT THERE, HUH?
AND YOU KICKED THE BALL
REALLY GOOD, TOO.
YEAH, THAT, TOO.
YOU NAILED
THAT SHOT, DAVIS.
HEY, YOU GUYS ONLY LEAD
BY ONE GOAL.
KEN COULD STILL
SHOW UP.
IF HE WAS HERE RIGHT NOW,
I'D SHOW HIM --
Girls: IT'S HIM!
[ GIRLS GIGGLING ]
ME AND MY BIG MOUTH.
Girl: HE'S SO CUTE.
IT'S KEN!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
I MUST BE DREAMING.
SOMEBODY PINCH ME. OW!
HE'S LOOKING RIGHT AT US.
OH, I'M GOING TO FAINT!
[ Thinking ] SO THAT'S
WHAT ALL THE FUSS IS ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE DOESN'T LOOK SO TOUGH.
FOR ALL THE ATTENTION
HE'S GETTING,
THAT GUY SURE KNOWS
HOW TO KEEP HIS COOL.
Davis: HEY, I'M COOL.
MORE LIKE LUKEWARM.
THAT'S SO FUNNY,
I FORGOT TO LAUGH.
HEY, KEN, WE'RE REALLY GLAD
YOU COULD MAKE IT TODAY.
SORRY I'M A LITTLE LATE,
BUT THERE WAS SOMETHING
I HAD TO DO FIRST.
WE'RE JUST HAPPY YOU FOUND
THE TIME FOR US.
CAN I PUT YOU
IN THE GAME NOW?
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
NOW SUBSTITUTING, NUMBER 7 --
KEN "THE ROCKET" ICHIJOUJI.
YOU MUST BE KEN. I'M DAVIS.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HMM.
HE LOOKED RIGHT AT ME!
CAN YOU BELIEVE HE'S
EVEN CUTER IN PERSON
THAN HE IS ON TV?
I COULD JUST HUG HIM ALL DAY.
HE'S NOT
AN ACCORDION, YOLEI.
HE'S JUST A KID
LIKE YOU, DAVIS!
YOU GOTTA OUTRUN HIM!
YOU CAN DO IT,
AND EVEN IF YOU CAN'T,
WE WON'T THINK
ANY LESS OF YOU, MAN.
SOME NICE FRIENDS
YOU GOT THERE, DAVIS.
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
HUH?
WHOA. NO WONDER
THEY CALL HIM "THE ROCKET."
DID YOU CATCH THAT MOVE?
Kari: HE'S FANTASTIC.
Yolei: BACK OFF.
I SAW HIM FIRST.
GOAL SCORED BY "THE ROCKET"!
HOUSTON, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
HE'S SO AMAZING,
AND DID I MENTION DREAMY?
WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO PINCH YOU AGAIN?
YOLEI ICHIJOUJI.
KEN AND YOLEI ICHIJOUJI.
NOW THAT KEN'S
TIED UP THE GAME,
I WONDER HOW IT'S GOING
TO AFFECT DAVIS' CONFIDENCE.
WHOA!
HOW'D HE DO THAT?
DAVIS ISN'T LOOKING
TOO GOOD OUT THERE.
OUCH.
KEN'S RUNNING CIRCLES
AROUND HIM.
IT'S LIKE DAVIS
ISN'T EVEN THERE.
EASY AS SHOOTING GOALS
INTO AN EMPTY NET.
KEN HAS MORE
THAN JUST SKILL.
HE LEADS HIS TEAM LIKE
A GENERAL LEADS AN ARMY.
[ CHEERING ]
HE'S NOT JUST GOOD,
HE'S GREAT.
STICK TO THE PLAYBOOK
I WROTE, EVERYBODY.
ALL FULLBACKS AND MIDFIELDERS,
MOVE UP!
♪ YOU RUN AROUND,
I RUN AROUND ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL GONNA
RUN, RUN, RUN AROUND ♪
All: GO, ROCKET, GO!
NO!
HAVE A GOOD TRIP, KEN.
SEE YOU NEXT FALL.
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
TIME'S RUN OUT,
AND THE GREEN TOMACHI TEAM,
LED BY
KEN "THE ROCKET" ICHIJOUJI,
WINS 9 TO 1.
[ CHEERING ]
HEY, KEN,
IS YOUR LEG ALL RIGHT?
SORRY ABOUT THAT TACKLE.
I GUESS I CAUGHT YOU OFF GUARD.
I BARELY FELT IT.
TOO BUSY THINKING
ABOUT SCORING GOALS.
YOUR TEAMMATES
PROBABLY TOLD YOU
ABOUT HOW I WAS DOMINATING
THE FIELD,
HOW UNSTOPPABLE I WAS
BEFORE YOU GOT HERE.
SOMEONE MAY HAVE MENTIONED
SOMETHING ABOUT YOUR PLAY.
IF YOU KEEP IT UP,
YOU MIGHT WIN A CHAMPIONSHIP.
ONCE YOU GUYS GOT
SO FAR AHEAD,
I FIGURED IT WAS
ALL OR NOTHING,
SO I WENT FOR IT
ON THAT LAST PLAY.
I WAS OBVIOUSLY FOCUSED
ON SCORING ANOTHER GOAL
AND DIDN'T SEE YOU COMING.
THAT PLAY NEVER FAILS.
WELL, IT DID AGAINST ME.
WELL, MY WORTHY ADVERSARY,
FAREWELL.
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN
IN BATTLE.
WORTHY ADVERSARY?
THEN WE SHOOK HANDS
AND HE SAID HE ADMIRED ME.
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
THIS HAPPY ABOUT LOSING.
IT WASN'T SO BAD.
AND GUESS WHAT --
HE CALLED ME
HIS WORTHY ADVERSARY.
"THE ROCKET" PRACTICALLY SAID
I'M AS GOOD AS HE IS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
DIDN'T GET ME HIS AUTOGRAPH.
THAT SLIDING BLOCK YOU DID
WAS ULTRA-COOL, DAVIS.
YEAH, COOL.
IT MADE
MY TOOTH TINGLE.
I BET YOU THAT KEN AND I
ARE GOING TO BE
ON THE SAME CHAMPIONSHIP TEAM
SOMEDAY.
I THINK YOU'RE GETTING
AHEAD OF YOURSELF.
HOW ABOUT YOU TRY SCORING
AT LEAST ONE GOAL AGAINST HIM?
VERY FUNNY, TAI,
BUT I GUESS YOU GOT A POINT.
I'LL HAVE TO TRY THAT.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
Ken: [ Thinking ]
HA HA HA.
GO AHEAD,
LAUGH WHILE YOU'RE STILL ABLE,
FOR THE TIME DRAWS CLOSER
TO WHEN YOU SHALL
BOW BEFORE ME.
NO ONE IS MY EQUAL,
AS YOU SHALL FIND OUT.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
WHY?
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
BECAUSE I SAID SO.
HUH? HERE YOU GO.
SINCE YOU SHOOK HANDS
WITH KEN,
IF I SHAKE HANDS WITH YOU,
IT'LL BE ALMOST LIKE
I'M SHAKING HANDS WITH HIM.
OH!
OH, I CAN'T DO IT.
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
I'LL WAIT TO SHAKE HANDS
WITH MY BELOVED IN PERSON.
All: OH, BROTHER.
JUST WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, CODY?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU'RE DREAMING.
LET ME PINCH YOU.
IT'S A CONTROL SPIRE.
WHAT'S IT DOING THERE?
CONTROLLING, SPIRING --
THE USUAL.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN BUILT
OVERNIGHT. AMAZING.
SO JUST WHERE
IS IT LOCATED?
THIS MAP DOESN'T LIST
THE POINTS OF INTEREST.
IT'S THE FORBIDDEN VALLEY
OF NO RETURN.
WHY DO BAD GUYS ALWAYS
NAME THINGS LIKE THAT?
IT'S IN THE JOB DESCRIPTION
AFTER "REALLY STINKY BREATH."
EVEN IF THIS WAS THE VALLEY
OF DUCKIES AND BUNNIES,
WITH THE CONTROL SPIRE THERE,
THERE'S TROUBLE.
WE'VE GOT TO DESTROY IT
BEFORE IT'S USED
TO CONTROL
ALL THE DIGIMON, YEAH?
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S GO, DAVIS!
ARE YOU REALLY SURE
ABOUT THIS?
DIGIPORT, OPEN.
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH-OH-OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
WOW, THIS VALLEY SURE
LOOKS FORBIDDEN, ALL RIGHT.
A FEW DUCKIES AND BUNNIES
WOULD SPRUCE IT UP.
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR COULD
BE AROUND HERE ANYWHERE,
SO STAY SHARP.
LET'S STAY TOGETHER.
I THINK THIS VALLEY
IS QUAINT AND HOMEY.
MORE LIKE HOMELY.
QUIET. WE DON'T WANT
THE EMPEROR TO HEAR US.
AAH!
I BET HE HEARD THAT.
All: WHOA!
GUYS! DID YOU SEE THAT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
THE GROUND
JUST ATE OUR FRIENDS.
MAYBE IT'LL
SWALLOW US NEXT.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
I THINK YOU BETTER CALL TAI
TO HELP US OUT.
NO WAY, VEEMON.
THAT'LL TAKE WAY TOO LONG.
HELP ME DIG BEFORE
WE FIND MORE TROUBLE.
Emperor: MORE TROUBLE
HAS FOUND YOU.
DIGIMON EMPEROR,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
WHERE ARE MY FRIENDS?
YOUR FRIENDS
ARE HERE WITH ME.
COME AND SEE
IF YOU DARE.
RUN, VEEMON.
THE GROUND COULD OPEN UP
AND SWALLOW US ANY SECOND.
I WANTED TO START
GETTING MORE EXERCISE,
BUT RUNNING FOR MY LIFE
WASN'T WHAT I HAD IN MIND.
I'M MORE WORRIED
ABOUT OUR FRIENDS RIGHT NOW.
THE EMPEROR'S VOICE
CAME FROM THIS DIRECTION.
THERE HE IS.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET IT!
HA HA HA HA!
OH, I AM SO SCARED.
LET MY FRIENDS GO!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH THEM?
TAKE A LOOK. YOUR FRIENDS
ARE AT MY MERCY,
AND SO, IT WOULD APPEAR,
ARE YOU.
OH, NO. GUYS!
DAVIS, SAVE YOURSELF!
RUN! YOU CAN STILL ESCAPE!
DON'T TAKE YOUR EYES
OFF THE EMPEROR.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
SAVE ME.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
YOUR TIME IS RUNNING SHORT.
WHOOPS, TIME'S UP.
OH, NO!
AWAKEN, DELTAMON.
MAYBE IT'S A DUCKY
OR A BUNNY. OR NOT!
[ GROWLING ]
JUST WHAT IS THAT THING,
VEEMON?
DELTAMON IS
A DRAGON-TYPE DIGIMON
WITH A METAL HEAD FOR ONE HAND
AND A SKULL FOR THE OTHER.
HIS ATTACKS ARE TRIPLEX FORCE
AND TRIPLE BITE.
WHAT LUCK
THAT YOU ALL DROPPED BY.
IT'S DELTAMON'S DINNER TIME,
AND EATING ALL OF YOU
WILL MAKE
A WELL-BALANCED MEAL.
OH, NO, YOU WON'T.
I'LL NEVER LET YOU
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
IT APPEARS
THAT YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
IF YOU WANT ME
TO SHOW MERCY,
YOU MUST BEG FOR IT.
YOU HEARD ME,
PATHETIC LOSER.
ON YOUR KNEES AND BEG,
"PLEASE, MASTER,
SPARE MY FRIENDS."
[ GROANS ]
DON'T, DAVIS.
PLEASE, MASTER,
SPARE MY FRIENDS.
"PLEASE, MASTER,
SPARE MY WORTHLESS FRIENDS."
PLEASE, MASTER,
SPARE MY WORTHLESS FRIENDS.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
NOW, VEEMON, RESTRAIN HIM.
I COMMAND YOU!
NEVER!
IT'S OKAY, VEEMON.
DO WHAT HE SAYS.
DAVIS --
IF IT'LL SAVE OUR FRIENDS,
OBEY THE EMPEROR.
[ SOBBING ]
HA HA HA HA!
SEEING YOU SQUIRM
IS SO DELICIOUS.
MAYBE I SHOULD TAKE PITY
ON YOU.
AS YOU CAN SEE, DELTAMON
HAS ONLY THREE MOUTHS,
BUT THERE ARE FOUR CHILDREN.
THEREFORE,
YOU MAY HAVE ONE.
SADLY, I CANNOT
SPARE THEM ALL.
CHOOSE WHO WILL BE SPARED.
SO I HAVE TO CHOOSE?
[ ROARS ]
HOW DO I PICK ONE
OVER THE OTHERS?
THIS MUST BE DONE
DELICATELY.
YOU HAVE UNTIL
THE SANDS RUN OUT
TO CHOOSE,
AND IT ISN'T LONG,
PRETTY BOY.
IT ISN'T LONG.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
SAVE ONE OF THE OTHERS.
GET OUT OF HERE, DAVIS.
GO AHEAD, SAVE YOURSELF.
OH, SURE,
MAKE ME LOOK BAD.
FINE, THEN DON'T SAVE ME.
WHATEVER YOU DECIDE TO DO,
WE TRUST YOU,
SO THINK OF SOMETHING.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT I SHOULD DO.
THE SAND'S RUNNING OUT.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO CHOOSE
ONLY ONE OF MY FRIENDS
AND SACRIFICE
ALL THE REST?
LIKE SANDS IN THE HOURGLASS,
SO ARE YOUR FRIENDS' LIVES.
I JUST --
I-I CAN'T DO IT.
WILL YOU THROW
ALL THEIR LIVES AWAY?
IS THAT WHAT YOU
CALL FRIENDSHIP?
THEY'RE ALL MY FRIENDS!
[ Thinking ]
KARI...T.K...
CODY...YOLEI...
AAH!
HA HA HA HA!
[ Thinking ]
YOU BROUGHT THIS ON YOURSELF.
YOU MADE ME LOOK
LIKE A FOOL.
NOW YOU MUST SUFFER.
HUH?
AND NOW, DIGIDESTINED,
TIME'S UP.
IT'S TIME TO SAY GOODBYE.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ROARING ]
WAIT! TAKE ME
INSTEAD OF THE OTHERS!
HMM. YOU THINK YOU
CAN SATISFY HIS HUNGER?
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
DELTAMON!
[ ROARS ]
LOOK OUT, DAVIS!
DAVIS, IF YOU'VE BEEN
HOLDING BACK
AND PLANNING
A SURPRISE ATTACK,
NOW WOULD BE A GOOD TIME
TO YELL "SURPRISE."
SURPRISE.
VERY FUNNY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SURPRISE? IT ISN'T EVEN
MY BIRTHDAY.
IT'S DIGMON.
INCOMING!
PEGASUSMON, HALSEMON,
NEFERTIMON.
IT'S AN ILLUSION.
WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
BUT IF YOU'RE HERE,
WHO'S THAT?
EW, GROSS.
WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
Veemon: DESPITE THEIR OBVIOUS
DENTAL HYGIENE PROBLEMS,
BAKEMON ARE ABLE
TO ACCURATELY IMPERSONATE
ANY OTHER CREATURE.
THEIR ATTACK IS CALLED
THE DARK CLAW.
HE MADE THE BAKEMON
LOOK LIKE OUR FRIENDS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
YOU DUMB BAKEMON.
I HAD THAT KID
RIGHT WHERE I WANTED HIM!
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
PULLED THAT TRICK ON ME.
GO GET HIM, VEEMON.
IT'LL BE MY PLEASURE.
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON, ARMOR-DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON,
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
BAKEMON, YOU GAP-TOOTHED FOOLS,
ATTACK!
NOT ME, THEM!
HERE THEY COME!
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
LIKE MOSQUITOES.
ATTACK THEM!
I NEVER SAW MOSQUITOES
DO THAT.
THE EMPEROR
IS CONTROLLING THEM.
THE DARK RINGS THE BAKEMON
ARE WEARING ARE THE KEY.
HE'S ORDERING THEM AROUND LIKE
A GENERAL LEADING HIS ARMY.
I'M GOING TO GET THAT GUY.
AAH!
BAKEMON, FINISH THEM!
I HAVE THEM NOW.
NEVER!
I'LL STAY
AND GUARD THE HILL.
YOU TRIED TO TAKE OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND DESTROY ME.
WELL, I'M TAKING YOU
WITH ME.
YOU CALL YOURSELF
A DIGIMON EMPEROR?
WHAT'S WITH THAT?
I AM A GENIUS.
I CANNOT LOSE
TO A CHILD LIKE YOU.
YOU ARE LIKE ME.
YOU'RE A KID JUST LIKE US.
I THINK NOT.
DELTAMON, TRIPLEX FORCE!
[ ROARING ]
SAY GOODBYE.
HA HA HA HA!
HELLO.
FLAMEDRAMON.
WHY LEAVE SO SOON?
THE PARTY'S JUST STARTING.
[ ROARING ]
FIRE ROCKET!
FLAMEDRAMON,
AIM FOR THE DARK RING!
[ GROANING ]
IT'S WORKING.
THE EMPEROR'S POWER OF
THE BAKEMON IS WEAKENING.
IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE
TO ATTACK.
STAR SHOWER!
AAH!
TARGET THE CONTROL SPIRE.
TEMPEST WING!
ROSETTA STONE!
GOLD RUSH!
THERE SHE BLOWS!
All: THEY DID IT!
THEY SURE DID! YES!
NO. NO!
WHAT WENT WRONG?
MY MASTER PLAN
WAS INVINCIBLE!
I'VE NEGLECTED TO FACTOR IN
THAT YOU'RE
ONE OF THOSE
ALL-OR-NOTHING TYPES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE SAME PERSON
MADE ME LOOK
LIKE A FOOL TWICE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN TWICE?
HEY, HOW'D YOU GET
THAT CUT ON YOUR LEG?
WAIT, ARE YOU --
COULD YOU POSSIBLY BE --
I COULD AND I AM.
KEN ICHIJOUJI.
OH, I'M DREAMING.
KEN IS THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
THE ONE AND ONLY.
WELL, DAVIS, FAREWELL FOR NOW,
MY WORTHY ADVERSARY.
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN
IN BATTLE.
[ ROARS ]
I REALLY
LOOKED UP TO YOU, KEN.
I DREAMED OF BEING
JUST LIKE YOU SOMEDAY.
NOW THAT I KNOW
YOU'RE MY SWORN ENEMY,
ALL I CAN SAY IS --
AND I MEAN THIS --
YOU CAN KEEP
YOUR CRUMMY AUTOGRAPH!
NOW THAT KEN'S SECRET
IS REVEALED,
CAN THE DIGIDESTINED FIND A WAY
TO DEFEAT HIM?
KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."