GREAT PARTY, HUH?
Girl: YEAH. MIMI THROWS
THE BEST PARTIES.
HEY, SUSIE,
WANT TO DANCE?
GREAT. LET'S GO.
WE HAD A GREAT TIME, MIMI.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
OKAY. SEE YOU.
DADDY!
HMM,
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
WE'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO TRAVEL
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
WITHOUT OUR DIGIVICES
OR D-3s,
BUT SOMEHOW KARI DID,
AND NOT ONLY
DID SHE NOT HAVE HER D-3,
SHE WAS TRANSPORTED THERE
WITHOUT GOING THROUGH ANY GATE.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
SPECIAL ABOUT KARI
THAT WE'RE NOT AWARE OF.
HUH? AN E-MAIL.
IT'S FROM YOLEI.
"THERE'S A DIGIEGG NEARBY.
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP COOKING."
GOING TO KEEP COOKING?
WELL, WHATEVER YOU'RE MAKING,
BE SURE AND SAVE ME SOME.
"SORRY, IT WAS A TYPO.
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP LOOKING."
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
THERE ARE NO CONTROL SPIRES
IN THAT AREA,
SO FEEL FREE
TO TAKE YOUR TIME.
HMM? WHOA, A DIGIPORT
HAS OPENED IN AMERICA.
HEY, WAIT,
MIMI LIVES THERE,
BUT IT'S NOT EVEN
MORNING THERE YET.
I CAN'T CALL HER. LET'S SEE.
I'LL SEND HER AN E-MAIL.
OH, I CAN'T WALK
ANOTHER STEP.
I GOT
TO EAT SOMETHING NOW.
YEAH, I'M GETTING
KIND OF HUNGRY, TOO.
BUT WE'RE VERY CLOSE
TO FINDING THE NEW DIGIEGG.
WHEN WE FIND THAT DIGIEGG,
I'M GOING TO EAT IT.
YOU'LL DO NO SUCH THING,
AND BESIDES,
YOUR CHOLESTEROL
IS TOO HIGH.
Kari: IF WE WANT TO EAT,
WE'LL HAVE TO GO BACK.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
Cody: SO LONG, DIGIEGG.
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE LAKE,
I THINK IT'S A RESTAURANT.
A RESTAURANT!
WE'RE SAVED AT LAST!
Man's voice: WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SIT IN THE DIGIVOLVING
OR NON-DIGIVOLVING SECTION?
Both:
THAT WAS DELICIOUS!
I'M GOING TO RECOMMEND
THIS RESTAURANT
TO ALL MY FRIENDS
WHO DINE IN THE DIGIWORLD.
Kari: WHAT'S WRONG, T.K.?
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS PLACE
IS REALLY BOTHERING ME.
I FEEL LIKE
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE
AND IT WASN'T GOOD.
MAYBE LAST TIME
YOU ORDERED
THE WRONG THING.
WAITER, WE'RE READY
FOR OUR CHECK.
OKAY,
HOLD YOUR HORSES.
AFTER ALL,
I'VE ONLY GOT ONE SHELL.
WHAT'S OUR BILL COME TO?
87 DIGIDOLLARS PLUS TIP.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM --
DON'T YOU HAVE ANY MONEY?
WE DON'T HAVE DIGIDOLLARS,
BUT WE HAVE PLENTY OF MONEY.
FORGET IT.
BUT OUR MONEY
IS JUST AS GOOD.
SINCE THE DARK MASTERS LEFT,
WE ONLY ACCEPT DIGIDOLLARS.
T.K.: WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
THE LUNKHEADED WAITER
WON'T TAKE MY MONEY.
I SEE YOU'RE BEING
YOUR USUAL BLUNT SELF.
I'M TRYING TO BE HONEST.
I THINK YOU KIDS ARE TRYING
TO SKIP OUT ON THE BILL.
I TOLD YOU -- WE HAVE $87.
ONLY DIGIDOLLARS
OR THE DIGI EXPRESS CARD.
THAT'S IT!
I'M NOT GOING TO RECOMMEND
THIS RESTAURANT TO ANYONE.
GOOD.
I DON'T WANT ANY HUMAN WORLD
DEADBEATS IN HERE.
NO WONDER THE FRENCH
HATE TOURISTS.
NOW, ARE YOU GOING
TO WORK OFF YOUR BILL,
OR DO I HAVE TO
CALL A COP?
I THINK I'VE HEARD
SOMETHING LIKE THIS BEFORE.
CAN'T WE PAY
NEXT TIME WE'RE HERE?
THERE WON'T BE
A NEXT TIME!
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
IN HERE AGAIN!
NOW GET IN THE KITCHEN
AND START WASHING DISHES --
Boy: FEAR NOT.
I'LL PAY THEIR BILL.
HOW SWEET.
PRINCE CHARMING.
WHO ARE YOU?
THIS IS MICHAEL.
HE'S A FRIEND OF MINE
FROM AMERICA.
All: IT'S MIMI.
OH, MIMI, IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
IZZY SENT ME AN E-MAIL
SAYING THERE WAS A DIGIPORT
OPEN IN AMERICA.
SINCE MICHAEL'S
A GOOD FRIEND OF MINE,
I THOUGHT
I'D BRING HIM ALONG.
I WANT EVERYONE TO SAY HELLO
TO A GOOD FRIEND OF MINE, TOO.
MY NAME'S BETAMON.
BETAMON IS REALLY COOL.
HE LIVES IN THE WATER AND USES
HIS BETA SLUGGER ATTACK
TO WIPE OUT HIS ENEMIES.
Kari: PALMON, ARE YOU SURE
IT'S OKAY YOU'RE HERE?
WHAT ABOUT THE AREA
YOU WERE PROTECTING?
TENTOMON SAID
HE'D WATCH IT FOR ME.
Yolei: I DON'T UNDERSTAND
SOMETHING, MIMI.
HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO BRING
MICHAEL TO THE DIGITAL WORLD?
MICHAEL HAS A DIGIVICE
JUST LIKE US.
All: HUH?
Davis: WAIT A MINUTE.
IF HE HAS A DIGIVICE,
THEN HE'S A DIGIDESTINED.
RIGHT. HIS DIGIVICE
IS THE SAME AS MINE.
SO HE BECAME A DIGIDESTINED
IN AMERICA AT THE SAME TIME
OUR ORIGINAL GROUP
DID IN JAPAN.
TELL US SOMETHING,
MICHAEL,
ARE THERE MORE DIGIDESTINED
KIDS LIKE YOU IN AMERICA?
TELL US HOW YOU BECAME
A DIGIDESTINED.
AND TELL ME YOU'RE SINGLE.
EVERYTHING HAPPENED
FOUR SUMMERS AGO
WHEN I FIRST SAW GORILLAMON
IN NEW YORK.
THAT'S THE SAME TIME
MYOTISMON WAS
TAKING OVER TOKYO.
Kari: T.K.'s RIGHT.
MY, THAT'S STRANGE.
I WONDER IF THAT MEANS
WE ALL HAD AN ENCOUNTER
WITH THE DIGIMON
AT THE EXACT SAME TIME.
THAT'S WHEN I WAS
ON THAT AIRPLANE
THAT HAD TO MAKE AN EMERGENCY
LANDING IN THE WATER.
THAT'S WHEN I SAW
MY FIRST DIGIMON.
I REMEMBER THAT SUMMER.
I WAS ONE OF THE PEOPLE
BEING HELD BY THE BAKEMON.
I WISH I COULD SAY THAT SUMMER
WAS AS TERRIFYING FOR ME
AS IT WAS FOR YOU GUYS,
BUT IT WASN'T.
I DID SEND A BUNCH
OF E-MAILS
DURING THE BATTLE
WITH DIABORAMON.
Mimi: SO EVERYONE
WAS INVOLVED SOMEHOW.
IT'S LIKE
WE'RE ALL CONNECTED.
BUT THERE'S STILL
ONE QUESTION --
WHO'S GOING
TO PAY THE BILL?
DON'T WORRY.
THE ENTIRE MEAL IS ON ME.
THAT'S IT. NOW I REMEMBER
WHERE I SAW HIM.
HE USED TO BE ONE
OF MYOTISMON'S HENCHMEN.
HE MADE MATT AND JOE WORK
IN THE KITCHEN HERE.
HE GOT MAD WHEN MATT ASKED
IF HE COULD GET HALF PRICE
ON HIS MEALS.
I ADMIT IT,
I WAS A ROTTEN EGG,
BUT THAT WAS IN THE PAST.
AFTER THE DARK MASTERS
WERE DEFEATED,
I KNEW I HAD
TO BREAK OUT OF MY SHELL.
WE'RE ALL VERY PROUD
OF YOU.
DON'T YOU FEEL
BETTER ABOUT YOURSELF?
WELL, NOW THAT
YOU MENTION IT,
IT IS KIND OF NICE
MAKING AN HONEST LIVING.
IT SEEMS YOU'RE STILL
ONE OF THE BAD GUYS
AFTER THE WAY
YOU TREATED ME.
YOLEI,
EVERYONE GETS CRANKY.
IF HE SAYS HE'S CHANGED,
I BELIEVE HIM.
SOMETIMES IT'S EASY
TO GET CRANKY WITH YOU.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT HOW
I TREATED YOU LAST TIME.
[ Thinking ] HE HAD
A CHANGE OF HEART, HUH?
IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE THAT
WHEN HE WAS YELLING AT US
FOR TRYING TO EAT AND RUN.
IT'S OKAY, DIGITAMAMON.
I'M SURE YOU'RE NOT
A TOTAL LOSER ANYMORE.
HUH? I DON'T WANT YOUR PITY,
I WANT YOUR MONEY!
FORK IT OVER NOW!
HUH?
RELAX. DON'T GET UPSET.
SHE WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
BESIDES, WE ALWAYS INTENDED
TO PAY THE BILL.
IF YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
MORE PATIENT,
WE COULD HAVE AVOIDED
THIS WHOLE THING.
MY BRAIN'S BEEN
SCRAMBLED LATELY.
I'VE GOT TO LOOK
AT THE SUNNY SIDE --
I'VE GOT MY HEALTH,
AND SOMEDAY, I MIGHT EVEN
HAVE FRIENDS.
FORGET THE BILL.
IT'S ON ME.
MIMI, NO MATTER
WHO YOU MEET,
YOU BRING OUT THE BEST
IN EVERYONE.
PLUS, I SAVED YOU
SOME DIGIDOLLARS.
HA HA HA!
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE
HAS A CRUSH ON MIMI.
[ Thinking ] HOW COME
I NEVER GET THE CUTE GUY?
[ GASPS ]
All: [ GASP ]
IT MUST BE
AN EARTHQUAKE. RUN!
LOOK OVER THERE.
GRRAAH!
IT'S GORILLAMON!
GORILLAMON WAS THE DIGIMON
I SAW IN NEW YORK.
WATCH OUT
FOR HIS ENERGY CANNON ATTACK.
IT'LL DRIVE YOU BANANAS.
Mimi: HE'S GOT
A DARK SPIRAL.
I THOUGHT DARK SPIRALS
ONLY WORKED
ON ULTIMATE-LEVEL DIGIMON.
IF THEY CAN CONTROL
CHAMPION-LEVEL DIGIMON, TOO,
THEN THERE MUST BE
DIFFERENT KINDS.
ENERGY CANNON!
HEADS UP!
[ PANTING ]
DIGITAMAMON!
AAH!
[ Thinking ] DIGITAMAMON
TRIED TO PROTECT US.
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
GET HIM
BEFORE HE GETS US!
VEEMON, NOW!
PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO HANDLE THIS.
OKAY, BETAMON?
OKAY!
UHH!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
BETAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
SEADRAMON!
Mimi: WOW, MICHAEL.
SEADRAMON'S YOUR DIGIMON.
I STILL GET CHILLS
REMEMBERING HIS ICE BLAST
AND ICE-WINDER ATTACKS!
RAARR!
RRAAH!
NOW THAT THEY'RE IN THE WATER,
SEADRAMON WILL WIN.
ENERGY CANNON!
ICE BLAST!
HE'S IN TROUBLE.
PALMON, YOU BETTER DIGIVOLVE
AND HELP SEADRAMON.
READY WHEN YOU ARE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PALMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
TOGEMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
LIGHT-SPEED JABBING!
TOGEMON, YOU DID IT.
RAAH!
VICTORY AT LAST.
SORRY WE HAD TO
TREAT YOU SO ROUGH.
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY TO GET
THAT DARK SPIRAL OFF YOU.
YOU SHOULD BE SAFE. STAY AWAY
FROM THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
THANKS.
WITHOUT THAT DARK SPIRAL,
HE DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE A BAD LITTLE MONKEY.
I DON'T THINK ANY DIGIMON
IS BORN EVIL.
WHEN THEY GET
THOSE DARK SPIRALS,
THEY'RE NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR ACTIONS.
HOW DO YOU GET THEM?
REMEMBER WHEN I TOLD YOU
ABOUT THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
HE CAPTURES THE DIGIMON
AND MAKES THEM HIS SLAVES.
WHY WOULD A YOUNG KID
WANT TO TAKE OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD
WHEN HE COULD BE PLAYING POLO
OR PRACTICING THE VIOLIN?
TO HIM IT'S A HOBBY.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
MY HOBBY?
BOYS DON'T COUNT,
YOLEI.
WHO ASKED YOU?
[ Gasps ]
HEY, WHERE'S
DIGITAMAMON?
HE TRIED TO PROTECT US
AND NOW HE'S GONE.
HE COULD BE ALL ALONE SOMEWHERE,
SCARED AND HURT.
KARI AND I WILL GO OFF
AND LOOK FOR HIM.
MM-HMM.
I'M SURE THEY'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND THEM IN NO TIME.
I HOPE SO.
[ GRUNTS ]
IS THIS FAST ENOUGH?
Mimi: DIGITAMAMON,
ARE YOU OKAY?
YES, NO THANKS TO YOU.
WE'RE SO GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
YEAH, WELL, DON'T BE
BECAUSE NOW
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU PAY!
[ Thinking ]
I KNEW HE WAS A BAD EGG.
WHO WANTS TO BE
DESTROYED FIRST?
BUT, DIGITAMAMON,
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS.
YOU TRIED
TO PROTECT US.
MIMI! CAREFUL.
HE'S ACTING DIFFERENTLY NOW.
YOU'RE EGGS-ACTLY RIGHT.
BEFORE I WAS SOFT AND RUNNY,
BUT NOW I'M HARD-BOILED.
I KNEW IT!
NOTHING CAN PENETRATE
MY SHELL,
AND WHEN I POACH MY ENEMIES
WITH MY NIGHTMARE
SYNDROMER ATTACK,
THEIR MINDS GET CRACKED!
WATCH OUT, MIMI!
WELL, YOLEI?
MM-HMM.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HAWKMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
HALSEMON --
THE WINGS OF LOVE.
WE BETTER HELP.
Both: DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
VEEMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE.
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER.
FIRE ROCKET!
HUH?
ROCK CRACKIN'!
I NEED
AN EGG-CRACKING ATTACK.
NONE OF OUR ATTACKS
ARE WORKING ON HIM.
Mimi: WAIT!
YOU GUYS HAVE TO LEAVE
DIGITAMAMON ALONE.
DIGITAMAMON, YOU'RE BEING
CONTROLLED BY SOMETHING EVIL.
REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID TO US
IN THE RESTAURANT --
THAT YOU'RE NOT
LIKE THAT ANYMORE?
I'M NOT BEING CONTROLLED.
THE ONE IN THE RESTAURANT
WAS A FAKE.
THIS IS THE REAL ME.
I REFUSE TO BELIEVE THAT.
THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM.
LET US ATTACK HIM.
NO, I'M SURE IF I CAN
JUST TALK TO HIM,
HE'LL COME AROUND.
HE'S EVIL.
LET'S SCRAMBLE
THAT EGG.
I HAVE TO TRY.
[ Thinking ]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND MIMI.
WHY IS SHE DOING THIS?
DIGITAMAMON
IS NOT EVEN OUR FRIEND.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU SAID ONE DAY
YOU HOPED TO HAVE FRIENDS?
WELL, TODAY IS THAT DAY
BECAUSE WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS.
FRIENDS? NO, THAT WAS
JUST A TRICK,
JUST LIKE WHEN I SAID,
"FORGET THE BILL."
WHICH REMINDS ME --
YOU STILL OWE ME
87 DIGIDOLLARS.
I DON'T CARE
HOW ROUGH AND TOUGH
YOU TRY TO ACT ON THE OUTSIDE,
DEEP DOWN INSIDE,
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT EVIL.
QUIT TRYING
TO BUTTER ME UP.
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE,
A PIECE OF TOAST?
STOP PRETENDING
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE FRIENDS.
OTHERWISE YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE TRIED TO PROTECT US.
YOU THINK I'M PRETENDING?
ARE YOU OKAY?
Mimi: I'M ALL RIGHT.
HE DIDN'T MEAN IT.
PLEASE, YOLEI,
DON'T HURT HIM.
I KNOW YOU CAN
GET THROUGH TO HIM.
BUT HE'S A PHONY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
TALK TO HIM.
IT WON'T BE EASY,
BUT I'LL TRY.
Digitamamon: OH, SO YOU WANT
A PIECE OF ME, TOO?
YOU THINK YOU'LL DO BETTER?
I'LL KNOCK YOU FOR A LOOP!
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANOTHER WORD FROM YOUR MOUTH!
DIGITAMAMON, YOU'RE THE RUDEST
DIGIMON I'VE EVER MET!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
AN OBNOXIOUS WAITER,
BUT WHEN YOU TOLD EVERYONE YOU
HAD A CHANGE OF PERSONALITY,
I GAVE YOU THE BENEFIT
OF THE DOUBT.
BUT WHEN YOU PUSHED MIMI,
THAT WAS THE LAST STRAW!
SHE WAS TRYING
TO MAKE YOU OUR FRIEND,
AND HOW DID YOU THANK HER?
BY VICIOUSLY ATTACKING HER
WITHOUT ANY CAUSE.
MIMI DOESN'T HAVE A MEAN BONE
IN HER BODY,
AND YOU COULDN'T SEE THAT.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I WILL NOT TOLERATE
THAT KIND OF BEHAVIOR
ANY LONGER.
YOU WANT TO BE FRIENDS
AND THEN CALL ME A PHONY.
I ADMIT I HAVE A PROBLEM
JUDGING OTHERS
BY MY FIRST IMPRESSION
OF THEM.
I SEE A CUTE-LOOKING BOY
AND I INSTANTLY FALL IN LOVE.
I NEVER STOP TO THINK WHAT KIND
OF PERSON THEY MIGHT BE.
THEY COULD BE COOL, LIKE T.K.,
OR A REAL JERK, LIKE DAVIS!
WELL, THOSE DAYS
ARE FINALLY OVER!
FROM NOW ON I PROMISE
TO BE AS SINCERE WITH PEOPLE
AS I POSSIBLY CAN.
AHH.
HUH? OH!
WAS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
IT'S THE NEW DIGIEGG.
IT'S GOT
THE CREST OF SINCERITY.
OHH.
IT MUST HAVE RESPONDED
TO YOLEI
WHEN SHE STARTED
TO TALK SO SINCERELY
ABOUT HER FEELINGS.
I GUESS SHE SINCERELY
THINKS I'M A JERK.
IT'S MY SECOND.
I'VE GOT TWO DIGIEGGS.
THEN LET'S USE IT.
MM-HMM.
DIGIARMOR ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HAWKMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
SHURIMON --
THE SAMURAI OF SINCERITY.
I AM SHURIMON.
AS HAWKMON, I USE THE DIGIEGG
OF SINCERITY TO ARMOR DIGIVOLVE.
MY DOUBLE STARS ATTACK
IS DOUBLE TROUBLE.
DOUBLE STARS!
NOT EVEN YOU
CAN PENETRATE MY SHELL.
NIGHTMARE SYNDROMER!
PROTECT YOLEI.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF DIGITAMAMON.
♪ I'M GOING DIGITAL ♪
DON'T LET IT GET THROUGH.
♪ NOW I'M INVINCIBLE ♪
WHAT'S HE LOOKING AT?
I SEE THE DARK SPIRAL.
IT'S INSIDE HIS SHELL.
DOUBLE STARS!
♪ DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
HEY, CAREFUL.
YOU ALMOST HIT ME IN HERE.
PEGASUSMON, NEFERTIMON,
GET HIM.
♪ I'M GOING DIGITAL ♪
Both: GOLDEN NOOSE!
HE'S TRYING TO GET AWAY!
NOT IF WE HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY ABOUT IT.
♪ LET'S ALL GET DIGITAL ♪
NOW TO TAKE CARE
OF THAT DARK SPIRAL.
DOUBLE STARS!
[ COUGHS ]
Yolei: HE COUGHED UP
THE SPIRAL.
THAT EGG IS OVER EASY!
Mimi: HE'S WAKING UP.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU HAD A DARK SPIRAL
IN YOU.
YOU -- YOU SAVED ME.
ACTUALLY,
YOLEI WAS THE ONE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
IT WAS ME?
I WANT TO THANK YOU,
YOLEI.
THERE'S NO NEED,
BUT I DO WANT TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THOSE THINGS
I SAID ABOUT YOU EARLIER.
I'M THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE APOLOGIZING.
FROM NOW ON I PROMISE NOT
TO JUDGE A BOOK BY ITS COVER.
AND I PROMISE NOT TO PUT
ALL MY EGGS IN ONE BASKET.
YEAH, THAT'S GREAT.
MIMI, THANKS TO YOU,
I'M GOING TO BE
TOTALLY HONEST WITH PEOPLE,
ESPECIALLY BOYS.
I WON'T BE FRIENDS WITH THEM
JUST 'CAUSE THEY'RE CUTE.
GREAT.
THEN NEITHER WILL I.
OH, MIMI.
IF YOU DON'T CARE
ABOUT LOOKS,
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO
ON A DATE WITH ME?
AAH!
I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO!
OOH, NOW I KNOW WHAT TO DO
IF SOMEONE ASKS ME OUT
ON A DATE.
Davis: WELL, MICHAEL, IT WAS
PRETTY COOL MEETING YOU.
I HOPE WE'LL GET TO HANG OUT
TOGETHER AGAIN REAL SOON.
Michael: THANKS.
I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
MIMI'S ALWAYS TELLING ME STORIES
ABOUT HOW GREAT ALL OF YOU ARE,
AND NOW I KNOW IT, TOO,
FIRSTHAND.
OH, BEFORE I GO,
THERE'S ONE THING I'VE WANTED
TO DO SINCE I GOT HERE.
YOLEI, I WANT
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WOULD LIKE TO GO OUT
ON A DATE WITH ME SOMETIME?
[ GIGGLES ]
GOODBYE, MICHAEL!
FRIDAY NIGHT'S GOOD,
OR ANY OTHER NIGHT WORKS, TOO.
WILL THEY ENCOUNTER
MORE DIGIDESTINED KIDS
FROM AROUND THE WORLD?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."