Davis: I TRIED TO TALK
THE OTHERS INTO GIVING KEN
A SECOND CHANCE,
BUT THEY WOULDN'T.
THEY DON'T TRUST HIM.
I'LL TELL YOU WHO I
DON'T TRUST --
THAT CRAZY WHITE-HAIRED LADY
PALMON SAW DOING SOMETHING
TO A CONTROL SPIRE.
SHE TURNED IT
INTO GOLMON.
HE TRIED TO DESTROY A DAM
AND FLOOD THE LOCAL TOWN.
OUR DIGIMON WERE FIGHTING
THE GOOD FIGHT,
BUT IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
YOLEI DIDN'T LIKE WHEN MIMI
AND I CALLED KEN FOR HELP.
WHEN SHE ADMITTED
SHE WAS WRONG ABOUT KEN,
HAWKMON DIGIVOLVED
INTO HIS CHAMPION FORM --
AQUILAMON.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HE HAD IT IN HIM.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Davis: OW, SHURIMON,
WATCH WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
YELL AT ME.
HE'S RIGHT --
WE NEED A REST.
I'M WITH YOU.
[ ALL SIGH ]
DO YOU HAVE
ANY WORCESTERSHIRE?
KARI, I WONDER,
DO YOU THINK IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT KEN'S
IN SOME KIND OF DANGER?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THAT WOMAN PALMON
WAS TELLING US ABOUT --
I JUST KNOW
SHE'S UP TO NO GOOD.
I THINK HE
MIGHT BE IN HER WAY.
Wormmon: LOOK
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, KEN --
AT LEAST NO ONE WILL EVER SAY
YOU THINK SMALL.
YOU CERTAINLY
HAVE A GOOD POINT.
JUST TRYING TO HELP.
DON'T TOUCH IT, IT'S --
PURE EVIL.
THEY'RE MY CREATION.
BUT EVEN I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW AROKINIMON CAN TAKE
ONE OF MY CONTROL SPIRES
AND SOMEHOW TURN IT
INTO A DIGIMON.
WHEN I WAS
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR,
I UNDERSTOOD THIS SORT
OF THING,
BUT NOTHING MAKES SENSE
TO ME NOW.
EARTH TO KEN --
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
YOU'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
THANKS, PAL. I'M GLAD SOMEONE
STILL HAS FAITH IN ME.
NOW I HAVE TO
HAVE FAITH IN MYSELF.
SINCE I WAS THE ONE
WHO BUILT THESE THINGS,
YOU'D THINK
I WOULD HAVE SOME CLUE
AS TO HOW THEY WORK,
BUT I DON'T.
AS DIGIMON EMPEROR
I WAS A GENIUS.
NOW I'M JUST PLAIN KEN.
THAT'S A RELIEF.
AS FAR
AS YOU'RE CONCERNED,
BUT WHAT
ABOUT THE DIGITAL WORLD?
THEY'LL GET OVER IT.
WORMMON...LOOKING
AT THESE THINGS
MAKES ME SICK
TO MY STOMACH.
OH, GREAT.
STICK YOUR HEAD
BETWEEN YOUR KNEES
AND TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
THIS WHOLE THING
IS MY FAULT.
AW...HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT?
THERE ARE PEOPLE YOU
CAN TALK TO ABOUT THIS.
THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU
TALK TO THEM
BEFORE BECOMING
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
IT HAD TO BE EASIER
THAN BUILDING CONTROL SPIRES.
EXCELLENT QUESTION,
WORMMON.
ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU CAN'T FIGURE OUT
HOW THEY WORK,
THEN I'LL JUST HAVE TO
KNOCK THEM ALL DOWN.
Cody: IT SEEMS
STURDY ENOUGH.
Davis: OF COURSE IT IS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ANYWAY?
DON'T YOU THINK
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING?
YOU SAID IT.
YEAH, EVEN IF IT IS
WHAT WE WERE THINKING.
THAT ROCK SLIDE THING
WASN'T MY FAULT.
IT WAS FLAMEDRAMON'S.
WAS NOT.
WAS TOO.
Gatomon: YOU WOULD MAKE
GOOD SCRATCHING POSTS.
THOSE MEDDLING KIDS.
JUST WHEN I HAD THE DIGIWORLD
SO DELICIOUSLY DESTROYED, TOO.
WHAT'S THIS, A SPLIT END?
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
INTOLERABLE.
[ GROANS ]
THAT'S ENOUGH.
NOW IT'S PERSONAL.
SPIRIT NEEDLE!
GO, THAT BRIDGE OFFENDS ME.
Flamedramon: YOU SAID, "GIVE ME
THE ROCK ON THE BOTTOM."
DID NOT.
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT DOES HE THINK
HE'S DOING?
Davis: HE'S HEADED
FOR THE BRIDGE.
Cody: MAYBE HE'S ADMIRING
THE DETAILED ARCHITECTURE.
OR A WAY TO BLOW
IT UP.
NOT AGAIN!
DAVIS!
YEAH!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
VEEMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
RAIDRAMON, THE STORM
OF FRIENDSHIP, GRRAAH!
EARTHQUAKE DRILL!
MINOTARUMON IS
A CHAMPION DIGIMON
WITH A NASTY LEFT JAB.
HIS EARTHQUAKE DRILL
WILL TURN THAT BRIDGE
INTO STEPPING STONES.
NOT MY BRIDGE. GET HIM!
THUNDER BLAST!
DAVIS...
TAKING A SWIM?
VERY FUNNY, T.P.
A LITTLE HELP HERE?
GRRAAH!
DAVIS IS GOING
TO MESS THIS UP AGAIN.
HAWKMON!
MY PLEASURE.
HAWKMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
AQUILAMON!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
AAH! OY VEY.
HOLD ON.
THAT THING'S
A CONTROL SPIRE.
IT'S NOT REAL.
IT'S REAL ENOUGH.
LET'S GET HIM.
YOU GOT IT.
YOU READY?
MM.
Both: DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
GATOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
PATAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
NEFERTIMON,
ANGEL OF LIGHT.
PEGASUSMON,
FLYING HOPE.
Both: GOLDEN NOOSE!
GRRAAH!
EARTH THUNDER BLAST!
AAH!
HA, NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
HUH?
All: OH, NO!
IT LOOKS LIKE HE TOOK
A BIG BITE OUT OF IT.
AW, I FEEL
SO VIOLATED.
WE STILL RESPECT YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT. WE'RE JUST
GOING TO REBUILD IT AGAIN.
IT'LL BE EASIER THIS TIME.
SHE'S RIGHT,
YOU KNOW.
WE REALLY LEARNED A LOT
FROM OUR MISTAKES.
THIS WILL GIVE YOU
THE CHANCE
TO MAKE NEW MISTAKES.
AW, BUT I LIKED
MY OLD MISTAKES BETTER.
HEY, SPEAKING OF MISTAKES,
WE SHOULD ASK KEN NOW.
All: KEN?
Davis: THANKS
FOR THE SUPPORT.
SERIOUSLY, I BET HE'D JUMP
AT THE CHANCE TO HELP US.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T TRUST HIM.
YOU MAY BE RIGHT,
BUT HE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN HELP.
WELL, I'M JUST NOT
COMFORTABLE AROUND HIM.
IT'S HARD FOR PEOPLE
TO REALLY CHANGE.
I THINK IT'S TOO RISKY.
YOU GOT A POINT,
BUT I HAVE A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT HIM, CODY.
REALLY?
BUT WHY, DAVIS?
THE DIGIEGG.
IF YOU HAD SEEN WHAT I SAW,
YOU'D BELIEVE IN HIM, TOO.
I MEAN, HIS CREST OF KINDNESS
TURNED INTO A GOLDEN DIGIEGG.
IT WAS THE MOST AMAZING THING.
YOU'RE GOING
TO THINK I'M CRAZY,
BUT YOU ALREADY
THINK I'M CRAZY, SO HERE GOES.
THAT DIGIEGG BELIEVED IN HIM.
IT WAS LIKE
IT WAS TELLING ME
I COULD BELIEVE, TOO.
IT ALMOST FELT LIKE
IT WAS ASKING ME
TO GO AHEAD AND TRUST HIM.
I KNOW THAT'S NOT VERY LOGICAL,
BUT NEITHER AM I.
ALL I KNOW IS
HE HAS THE CREST
OF KINDNESS FOR A REASON.
AND WHAT ABOUT HIS DIGIMON?
HE BELIEVES IN THEM, TOO.
I THINK BECAUSE WORMMON
KNEW WHAT WAS IN HIS HEART.
HE'S GOOD. I KNOW IT.
BUT WHAT IF YOU'RE WRONG,
DAVIS?
HE'S MADE IT CLEAR
HE DOESN'T WANT
TO BE PART OF OUR TEAM.
I KNOW,
BUT I'M AN OPTIMIST.
REALISTICALLY, HE COULD
STILL BE BAD TO THE BONE.
I THINK CODY'S RIGHT.
HE USUALLY IS.
[ Yawns ] I'M BORED,
AND ALL THIS TALK
ISN'T GETTING US ANYWHERE.
DON'T FORGET
THAT CRAZY WHITE-HAIRED CHICK
IS OUT THERE
AND UP TO NO GOOD.
[ Gasps ] WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S A MESSAGE
FROM IZZY.
I'M GETTING
A REAL BIZARRE SIGNAL.
IT'S NOT TOO FAR FROM YOU.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE SECTOR
WHERE KEN'S BASE WENT DOWN.
LET'S GET MOVING.
AND ANOTHER ONE
BITES THE DUST.
READY TO TAKE A BREAK,
STINGMON?
I GUESS I'VE WREAKED
ENOUGH HAVOC FOR ONE DAY.
I WANT A BATH.
NO OFFENSE,
BUT YOU REALLY NEED ONE.
Wormmon: PLEASE, KEN,
SLOW DOWN.
I HAVE AWFULLY SHORT LEGS,
YOU KNOW.
NOT TO PUT TOO FINE
A POINT ON IT --
THESE SPIRES YOU BUILT
HAVE SPLINTERS.
SORRY. THIS ISN'T EXACTLY
SUNDAY IN THE PARK, IS IT?
NOW, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
SEE, YOU'RE STILL A GENIUS.
LET'S HAVE SUNDAES
IN THE PARK.
THAT DOES SOUND GOOD.
WOULD YOU SETTLE
FOR HALF A JELLYROLL AT HOME?
YUMMY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Izzy: MY THEORY IS THAT
A MAJOR POWER SOURCE
IS ABOUT TO MELT DOWN.
IF YOU GUYS DON'T SHUT
IT DOWN FAST, IT'LL EXPLODE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, EXPLODE?
I MEAN EXPLODE,
YOU KNOW, BOOM.
THIS IS BAD,
BUT WHAT CAN WE DO?
OH...
THE CREST OF KINDNESS --
I'LL BET
IT'S BECAUSE KEN'S CREST
ISN'T THERE ANYMORE.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT ANYONE SAYS --
WE NEEDS KEN'S HELP,
AND WE NEED IT NOW.
BUT, DAVIS --
SHOULDN'T WE
TALK ABOUT THIS?
WE JUST DID.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO TRUST ME ON THIS.
I KNOW I'M RIGHT,
AND WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
HEY, KEN,
I FEEL QUEASY.
ME, TOO. LET'S SAVE
THE REST FOR LATER.
WHAT'S WRONG?
MY, MY, MY, NOW ISN'T THIS
JUST TOO DOMESTIC?
YOU AGAIN.
OH, PLEASE, KEN,
DON'T TALK TO HER.
DID I COME
AT A BAD TIME?
WELL, I'LL BE GOING.
BYE-BYE.
NO, WAIT!
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND THERE
IS BEING QUITE RUDE.
WHY SHOULD I?
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KEEPS CALLING ME!
WHAT DO YOU WANT
WITH ME?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I WANT ANYTHING FROM YOU?
THEN WHY
ARE YOU BOTHERING ME?
WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD?
WHY, KEN, WHAT A NOSY
LITTLE BOY YOU ARE.
THAT'S REALLY NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS, NOW, IS IT?
THIS IS CRAZY.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT US
TO DO, DAVIS?
WHERE'S KEN?
WHEN HE WAS THE EMPEROR,
WE WERE ALWAYS
TRIPPING OVER HIM.
OF COURSE
IT'S MY BUSINESS.
YOU'RE USING
MY CONTROL SPIRES --
MY CRE...ATION.
MY SHAME.
YOU THINK RATHER WELL
OF YOURSELF,
LITTLE BOY EMPEROR.
HUH?
"POOR ME. WHY DID I DO
SUCH AWFUL THINGS
WHEN I COULD HAVE USED
MY AWESOME POWERS FOR GOOD?"
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
HMM. TELEPHONE.
OH, KEN?
OH, YES,
YOU'RE SO SPECIAL.
GRR.
WHAT NOW?
ANY PRETTY LITTLE BOY
WOULD HAVE BEEN AS GOOD.
YOU USED ME.
OF COURSE I DID,
YOU LITTLE FOOL.
GRR.
TEMPER, TEMPER.
BUT YOU ALWAYS WERE
SO EASY TO MANIPULATE --
THE PERFECT TOY.
OH, I MEANT TO SAY "TOOL."
AND YOU THOUGHT
BUILDING THE CONTROL SPIRES
WAS YOUR IDEA. HA!
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I CAN'T TAKE THIS
ANYMORE.
HELLO,
ICHIJOUJI RESIDENCE.
I'M SORRY,
KEN'S BUSY RIGHT NOW.
WILL YOU PLEASE HANG UP
AND TRY YOUR CALL AGAIN LATER?
ARE YOU THE OPERATOR?
NO, I'M THE DIGIMON.
MAY I HELP YOU?
YOU MUST BE WORMMON.
YOU SEEM BRIGHT ENOUGH TO ME.
THANK YOU, I THINK.
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT ME?
OH, NEVER MIND!
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
I NEED TO SPEAK TO KEN
RIGHT AWAY.
HUMANS WITH SOMETHING TO PROVE
ARE PUTTY IN MY HANDS.
YOU WERE PARTICULARLY EASY
TO MOLD INTO SHAPE.
BUT WHY ME?
WHY DID YOU
HAVE TO MOLD ME?
"WHY ME?" REALLY,
YOU MUST STOP ASKING THAT.
I TOLD YOU --
IT WAS JUST A WHIM.
I AM NOT YOUR WHIM,
AND I AM NOT GOING TO LET YOU
GET AWAY WITH THIS!
BUT, YOU SEE,
I ALREADY HAVE,
AND THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN
DO ABOUT IT, POOR KEN.
OH, JUST HANG UP ON HER.
SHE'S NOT A NICE WOMAN,
AND THIS IS IMPORTANT.
THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS IN TROUBLE, KEN.
THEY NEED YOU RIGHT AWAY.
THAT BOY DAVIS
IS SENDING E-MAILS.
[ GROANS ]
YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS,
DIDN'T YOU?
MAYBE I DID.
YOU NEED TO GET
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
AND TAKE YOUR CREST.
I THINK DAVIS MAY
ACTUALLY BE RIGHT THIS TIME.
HIS THEORY IS THAT
THE POWER SOURCE OF YOUR BASE
CAN ONLY BE CONTAINED
BY YOUR CREST.
IT'S A GOOD THEORY.
OH, EMPEROR BOY...
I HAVE A LITTLE THEORY
OF MY OWN TO CHECK OUT.
HA HA HA HA HA.
VERY CLEVER,
BUT I'M STILL AHEAD OF YOU.
NOT FOR LONG.
ANOTHER ONE?
DO YOU THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
ALL MOVE BACK A LITTLE?
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
YOU'RE THINKING
TOO MUCH AGAIN.
THAT'S BECAUSE I HAVE TO
FIND A WAY TO END THIS.
SHE USED MY PAIN AND GUILT
TO CONTROL ME.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I'M GUILTY
OF TOO MUCH ALREADY.
MAMA, PAPA, WHERE'S SAM?
NOT THIS TIME!
IT'S GETTING WORSE!
SO WHERE'S KEN, HUH?
I'M SURE
HE'S ON HIS WAY.
DON'T COUNT ON IT.
Yolei: WHO INVITED HER?
MAYBE KEN SENT
HIS SECRETARY INSTEAD.
YOU CHILDREN ARE
ALL SO TERRIBLY RUDE,
ALWAYS INTERFERING
IN MY BUSINESS.
SPIRIT NEEDLE!
DESTROY THEM!
WELL,
NOW I'VE SEEN IT ALL.
HOW DOES SHE
DO THAT THING?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT SHE'S SURE GOOD AT IT.
OOKUWAMON
IS AN ULTIMATE DIGIMON.
STAY CLEAR OF HIS
DOUBLE SCISSOR CLAW ATTACK.
HE HAS A CUTTING
SENSE OF HUMOR.
IT'S SHOWTIME, GUYS.
GRRAAH!
VEEMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
X-VEEMON!
HAWKMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
AQUILAMON!
ARMADILLOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANKYLOMON!
V-LASER!
BLAST RINGS!
AAH!
TAIL HAMMER!
GRRAAH!
HE'D BE KITTY KIBBLE
IF I COULD BECOME ANGEWOMON.
YOU GO, GIRL.
YOU CAN'T,
SO YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
DO WHAT YOU CAN. GOT ME?
Both: MM-HMM.
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
GATOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
NEFERTIMON,
ANGEL OF LIGHT!
PATAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
DOUBLE SCISSOR CLAW!
HAWKMON, NO! STOP!
HAND OF FATE!
PATAMON!
ANGEMON'S ATTACK IS MOST
EFFECTIVE AGAINST EVIL DIGIMON.
THAT THING'S
NOT EVEN A DIGIMON.
GRRAAH!
DOUBLE SCISSOR CLAW!
AAH!
GRRAAH!
MY TURN?
HERO TIME, WORMMON!
WORMMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
STINGMON!
GRRAAH!
SPIKING STRIKE!
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
HUH?
DAVIS!
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
AND THEY DOUBTED ME.
WHERE'S YOUR CREST?
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
GREAT. COME ON.
GIVE IT HERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, DAVIS?
SAVING THE WORLD!
THIS IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE
TO GET HURT BECAUSE OF ME.
I CAN TAKE THIS
FROM HERE.
ARE YOU NUTS?
HE'S AN ULTIMATE.
SO? I'LL DO THIS ALONE.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO,
GET YOURSELF KILLED?
THAT'S A GENIUS MOVE.
IT'S MY BASE,
MY CREST, AND MY FAULT.
NO ONE ELSE IS GOING
TO DIE FOR MY MISTAKES.
UNDERSTAND?
WE KNOW THE RISKS.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
I WAS THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
I WAS A MONSTER.
AND I AM AS GUILTY AS KEN.
I DIDN'T STOP HIM.
YOU TWO NEED TO CHILL.
THE ONLY WAY I'LL FEEL
LIKE A HUMAN AGAIN
INSTEAD OF A MONSTER
IS TO ERASE ALL TRACE
OF MY EVIL, TO FIX THINGS,
AND THE ONLY WAY
TO DO THAT
IS WITH MY OWN HANDS.
BUT, KEN --
HE STILL HAS NIGHTMARES --
HORRIBLE ONES.
BUT THEN, MINE ARE WORSE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS TO ME
AS LONG AS I CAN
ACCOMPLISH MY GOAL.
ENOUGH!
I'M TIRED
OF YOUR BIG BAD WOLF ACT.
X-Veemon: HE MEANS
LONE WOLF.
THAT'S WHAT I MEAN.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU
DO THIS BY YOURSELF. GET IT?
WHAT ABOUT THE PEOPLE
WHO CARE ABOUT YOU?
AT LEAST
THINK OF YOUR DIGIMON.
WE'RE HERE, WE'RE HELPING,
AND THAT'S THAT.
WAKE UP, ICHIJOUJI!
YEAH, WAKE UP, STINGMON!
HERE'S YOUR CHANCE
TO STOP HIM
FROM DOING SOMETHING STUPID.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
YOU'RE THE GENIUS, KEN.
YOU FIGURE IT OUT.
IF I'M NOT HERE...
THEN WHAT?
DAVIS IS RIGHT.
HOW WILL YOU FIX YOUR MISTAKES
IF YOU'RE NOT HERE?
I MAY NOT BE
THE SHARPEST TOOL IN THE SHED,
BUT I KNOW THAT MUCH.
HMM. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS NEITHER OF US HAS
BEEN THINKING VERY CLEARLY.
OKAY, SO YOU MESSED UP
A FEW TIMES.
YOU THINK I HAVEN'T?
I DO IT ALL THE TIME.
DON'T GIVE UP.
FIX IT!
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
DO YOU THINK I DO?
YOU JUST KEEP TRYING
UNTIL SOMETHING WORKS,
AND WHEN IT GETS REALLY BAD,
YOU HANG WITH YOUR FRIENDS,
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALWAYS
YOUR FRIENDS,
EVEN WHEN YOU MESS UP.
GREAT. SO WHAT IF YOU DON'T
HAPPEN TO HAVE ANY FRIENDS?
[ GASPS ]
WHOA!
[ BOTH GASP ]
COOL! I CAN HEAR
MY HEART BEATING.
WAIT --
THAT'S KEN'S HEART.
SO THIS IS WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO HAVE A FRIEND.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
X-VEEMON!
STINGMON!
X-Veemon and Stingmon:
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
PAILDORAMON!
Both: PAILDORAMON?
THAT'S AMAZING.
WOW! I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
GRRAAH!
Narrator:
WILL THE COMBINED POWER
OF X-VEEMON AND STINGMON
BE ENOUGH TO STOP OOKUWAMON?
FIND ON SOON ON "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."