Man: CODY AND KEN
STILL WEREN'T SEEING EYE TO EYE,
SO YOLEI AND DAVIS
CAME UP WITH A BRAINSTORM
OF HOW TO GET THEM TOGETHER.
WORMMON AND ARMADILLOMON
BECAME GOOD FRIENDS.
CODY SAW THROUGH DAVIS
AND YOLEI'S LAMEBRAINED PLAN,
AND LET THEM HAVE IT.
KEN FELT LIKE HE WAS THE CAUSE
OF THE TROUBLE, SO HE LEFT.
ARUKINIMON USED
100 CONTROL SPIRES
TO CREATE BLACKWARGREYMON.
EVEN PAILDREMON
COULDN'T DEFEAT HIM.
ARUKINIMON
ORDERED BLACKWARGREYMON
TO DESTROY
THE ENTIRE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT HE SAID HE NO LONGER
TAKES ORDERS FROM ANYONE.
I HOPE HE'S ON OUR SIDE.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ ALL GASP ]
I'M INVISIBLE.
I'M NOT HERE.
YOU DON'T SEE ME.
[ GROANING ]
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO TRACK BLACKWARGREYMON
BY FOLLOWING
THE SPACIAL DISRUPTION.
HE WON'T ELUDE YOU,
MY SWEET.
YOU HAD BETTER BE RIGHT,
MUMMYMON,
AND DON'T CALL ME THAT.
I AM YOUR ETERNAL SLAVE,
MY DEAR. WHATEVER YOU WISH.
YOU'RE PATHETIC. SPEED UP.
I'M GROWING WEARY OF YOU.
YES, PUMPKIN.
WE NEEDED THIS
LIKE A HOLE IN THE HEAD.
I THINK THAT'S EXACTLY
BLACKWARGREYMON'S PLAN.
IF HE EVEN LOOKS
AT KARI THE WRONG WAY,
I'LL PUT A HOLE IN HIS HEAD.
I DON'T CARE IF HE IS A MEGA.
VERY COURAGEOUS,
BUT CRAZY.
EVEN IF YOU COULD
DIGIVOLVE TO ULTIMATE,
WHICH LET ME REMIND YOU --
YOU CAN'T --
HE'S TOO POWERFUL.
IF THE REST OF YOU COULD
DNA DIGIVOLVE, HE'D BE TOAST.
THINK YOU COULD HAVE MORE
OF AN ATTITUDE, LITTLE GUY?
HOW RUDE, BUT HE'S RIGHT.
WE'RE USELESS.
MAYBE WE COULD PRACTICE,
BUT WHO WITH?
YEAH,
WHO'S MY PARTNER?
GOOD QUESTION. YOU'RE ALL
SO YOUNG AND INEXPERIENCED.
BUT WE'LL LEARN QUICK.
YOU'LL HAVE TO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
BLACKWARGREYMON
DISSED ARUKINIMON LIKE THAT,
NOT THAT I BLAME HIM.
I THINK SHE WAS AS SURPRISED
AS WE WERE.
BLACKWARGREYMON
IS A LOOSE CANNON.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
HE'S GOING?
I KIND OF FEEL
SORRY FOR HIM.
[ ALL GASP ]
HE MUST BE VERY CONFUSED
AND LONELY.
SHE CREATED HIM
TO BE A FIGHTING MACHINE.
THAT JUST SEEMS
REALLY SAD TO ME.
I MUST BE GOING CRAZY.
IT SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE YOU'RE WORRYING ABOUT
A COLD-BLOODED MONSTER.
NOT REALLY.
I JUST CARE ABOUT HIM.
THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN YOU AND KARI --
SHE CARES
ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
IT'S STUPID
TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
LET'S GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND FINISH
WHAT WE STARTED.
IF WE KNOCK DOWN
THE CONTROL SPIRES,
OLD WHITE HAIR
IS OUT OF BUSINESS.
KARI, YOU'RE WITH ME,
AREN'T YOU?
YEAH.
I'M WITH YOU, DAVIS.
[ Thinking ]
I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT DAVIS MAY BE RIGHT
ABOUT KARI AND ME.
SHE NEVER PUTS HER FOOT
IN HER MOUTH LIKE I DO.
I NEVER KNOW
WHAT SHE'S THINKING.
IT KIND
OF MAKES ME NERVOUS.
SO, ANYWAY, THEN THE GUY SAYS,
"KNOCK, KNOCK" --
V-MON, I TOLD YOU --
NO MORE KNOCK-KNOCK JOKES.
IT'S ABOUT A GUY
WHO TELLS KNOCK-KNOCK JOKES.
NO MORE.
YOU'RE NO FUN.
THIS IS WEIRD.
Kari:
WHAT IS IT, GATOMON?
THIS IS IT.
I THOUGHT IT LOOKED FAMILIAR.
IT'S WHERE I LOST
MY TAIL RING.
REALLY? ARE YOU SURE?
POSITIVELY.
IT WAS AWFUL.
KEN WASN'T SO SWEET
BACK THEN,
AND EVEN GOOD DIGIMON WERE
FORCED TO DO HIS DIRTY WORK.
I COULDN'T LOOK
FOR MY RING BACK THEN,
BUT IF I HAD IT NOW,
I'D BE ONE TOUGH DIGIKITTY.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO GO FIND IT --
WHATEVER IT IS.
YOU'RE THE GREATEST.
TRYING TO WIN POINTS
WITH KARI?
LOOKS LIKE IT ACTUALLY
WORKED THIS TIME.
NOT EVEN DAVIS
CAN STRIKE OUT EVERY TIME.
OH, YES, I CAN.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT TO SAY.
YES, IT IS.
WHATEVER.
HE MAY BE CONFUSED,
BUT HE HAPPENS TO BE RIGHT.
THAT'S ONE POINT
FOR DAVIS.
TWO POINTS AND A COOKIE
IF YOU FIND IT.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
THANKS A LOT.
LET'S GET GOING,
KARI.
I THINK THAT CLEARING WE PASSED
IS THE BEST BET, YOLEI.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD WE START THERE?
OH.
WHAT?
BACK TO USUAL,
HUH, BUDDY?
THIS PLACE
JUST DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
LET'S GO HOME, KEN.
KEN, WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M NOT SURE.
[ GASPS ]
THIS IS MINE NOW!
AAH!
OH, NO, KEN. HELP!
THIS IS
EXCEEDINGLY TEDIOUS.
AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE BIRD'S-EYE VIEW.
AAH!
THAT'S KEN.
HE'S IN TROUBLE.
I HATE IT
WHEN SHE DOES THAT.
OH, KEN.
WAIT FOR ME!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR HIM SCREAM?
IT'S KEN. SOMETHING IS WRONG.
KEN?
DON'T WORRY, KEN.
WE'RE HERE NOW. IT'LL BE OKAY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WERE YOU ATTACKED?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
THE OCEAN...
HE'S FINALLY CRACKED.
IT WAS THE DARK OCEAN.
IT'S HORRIBLE.
HUH?
THE DARK OCEAN?
COULD IT BE?
MAYBE IT'S CONTAGIOUS.
I CAN'T SEE A THING.
HOW ABOUT YOU, HAWKMON?
IT'S NOTHING.
I'M FINE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT. YOU'RE
CLEARLY SEEING THINGS.
I THINK I KNOW
HOW YOU'RE FEELING.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
PLAY ALONG, HAWKMON.
DO YOU THINK
HE FELL ON HIS HEAD?
I DID THAT ONCE
AND THOUGHT I WAS A FRUIT BAT.
THIS IS HOPELESS.
WE CAN'T JUST GIVE UP.
NO WAY.
KARI IS COUNTING ON ME
TO FIND THIS THING FOR HER.
WHERE DID SHE
AND YOLEI GO?
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHAT?
THERE ARE THREE OF THEM?
WELL, WHO'S THAT WITH THEM?
HUH? THREE OF THEM?
THESE TREES ARE ALL BEGINNING
TO LOOK THE SAME --
TALL AND REALLY,
REALLY DARK.
DO YOU THINK
WE'VE BEEN CHASING
OUR TAIL THIS WHOLE TIME?
DO YOU THINK WE'RE LOST,
IS THAT IT,
FOREVER AND EVER
TILL WE DIE? HMM.
IT'S DAVIS.
WE'RE SAVED.
OVER HERE!
V-MON!
EXCELLENT TIMING.
DAVIS, T.K.!
HUH?
V-MON!
I FEEL FAINT.
I'M CONFUSED.
I WAS SURE
I HEARD A VOICE OVER HERE.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
THEY'RE GHOSTS, V-MON?
DAVIS,
WE'RE RIGHT HERE.
NO,
I DON'T BELIEVE IN THEM.
KARI, YOLEI!
THAT'S STRANGE.
IF WE CAN SEE HIM,
WHY CAN'T HE SEE US?
IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
CODY, T.K.,
DID YOU FIND KARI?
THEY HAVE JUST DISAPPEARED.
IT'S NOT LOGICAL.
THEY CAN'T HAVE GONE
THAT FAR.
EVEN I COULDN'T FIND THEM.
NOT ONE TRACE.
I'LL GO UP WITH PATAMON.
WE JUST HAVE TO TRY HARDER.
OKAY.
THEY'RE AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
WE'LL FIND THEM.
YOU READY,
ARMADILLOMON?
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
I DON'T LIKE THE WAY THIS FOG
KEEPS GETTING THICKER.
HEY, I KNOW,
LET'S SING A SONG.
OKAY, SO YOU DON'T
LIKE THAT PLAN.
WHY DON'T WE PLAY
A GAME?
HOW ABOUT THIS --
WE CAN PLAY
MY FAVORITE GAME --
TELEPHONE?
OH, I FORGOT --
THERE ARE ONLY THREE OF US.
I GUESS THAT WOULD BE
PRETTY BORING.
HOW ARE WE GOING
TO FIND OUR WAY HOME
IF WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE WE ARE? IT'S HOPELESS.
NOTHING IS
EVER HOPELESS, KEN.
THERE ARE TOO MANY PEOPLE
WHO WANT US BACK,
AND WE WANT
TO GO BACK TOO MUCH
TO BE STUCK HERE FOREVER.
WHY WON'T YOU
TALK TO ME?
DO YOU TWO WANT
TO BE ALONE OR SOMETHING?
YOU COULD JUST SAY SO INSTEAD
OF IGNORING ME LIKE THIS.
WE'RE NOT IGNORING YOU.
YES, YOU ARE.
COME BACK, YOLEI.
UM, YOLEI...
OH, I DID IT AGAIN,
DIDN'T I?
OH, HAWKMON,
WHATEVER WAS I THINKING?
THINKING IS PRECISELY
WHAT YOU DIDN'T DO.
KEN PROBABLY HATES ME
AFTER I MADE A FOOL OF MYSELF.
I DOUBT THAT.
UH-OH.
NOW WHAT?
KARI, GATOMON,
I THINK WE FOUND IT.
MY TAIL RING? REALLY?
SEE?
RIGHT DOWN THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
GATOMON?
I CAN'T TELL FROM HERE.
[ Thinking ]
I KNOW I'VE SEEN THIS BEFORE,
BUT WHERE?
THERE ARE TOO MANY GAPS
IN MY MEMORY.
WHY CAN I ONLY REMEMBER
THE AWFUL THINGS
AND NOT THE THINGS
THAT WOULD HELP SOMEONE?
IT ALMOST FEELS LIKE
IT'S ON PURPOSE.
[ Thinking ]
HE HAS THAT LOOK AGAIN.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
OH, YOLEI,
I BEG OF YOU -- DON'T.
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
IT'S TOO RISKY.
IT'S THE LEAST
I CAN DO -- WHOA!
I WISH YOU WOULDN'T DO
THIS SORT OF THING.
WELL, AT THIS EXACT MOMENT,
SO DO I.
DON'T WORRY.
I HAVE YOU.
[ GROANS ]
AAH!
YOLEI!
KARI!
NOT AGAIN.
AAH!
YOLEI, WAKE UP.
WHAT?
KARI, WHERE ARE WE?
THANK GOODNESS.
I WAS WORRIED.
ABOUT ME? WHY?
OH, YEAH, I REMEMBER SEEING
SOMETHING SHINING DOWN HERE,
BUT THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
THE USUAL.
YOU DID SOMETHING ABSURD.
BUT WE DID FIND THIS.
IT'S JUST A DARK RING.
I WAS TRYING SO HARD
NOT TO BE SELFISH FOR ONCE.
BUT YOU WEREN'T.
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
THE REAL THING. THANK YOU.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
NO, REALLY.
IT WAS VERY THOUGHTFUL.
IT WAS? ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
MY PLEASURE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HAWKMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
UH,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT SEEMS
I JUST CAN'T DO IT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN? THIS IS
NO TIME FOR JOKES, HAWKMON.
STOP FOOLING AROUND
AND DIGIVOLVE.
HOW CAN YOU
PICK ON ME LIKE THIS?
I JUST FELL FROM A CLIFF,
YOU KNOW?
HERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
IF YOU CAN'T DIGIVOLVE,
WE'LL NEVER GET OUT,
AND EVEN IF WE DO,
WHERE WILL WE GO?
WE'LL BE FINE.
HOW CAN WE BE FINE?
DAVIS RAN RIGHT THROUGH ME.
WE'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
NO, WE WON'T. MY LIFE IS OVER.
I'LL NEVER GET MARRIED,
HAVE CHILDREN, MAKE MILLIONS
IN THE STOCK MARKET.
I HATE THIS!
OH, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I NEEDED THAT.
BRUTAL, BUT EFFECTIVE.
NOW LET'S SEE IF WE CAN FIND
OUR WAY OUT OF THIS MESS.
I'M WITH YOU.
YOLEI, I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR SLAPPING YOU LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST NOT LIKE ME.
YOU SEEM TO BRING OUT
THE WORST IN ME.
MAYBE BECAUSE
WE'RE SO DIFFERENT.
NO, IT'S ME.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST, YOLEI.
THE TRUTH IS I ENVY YOU.
HUH?
I WISH I COULD SAY WHAT
I'M FEELING LIKE YOU DO.
I KEEP EVERYTHING INSIDE
SO NO ONE GETS HURT BUT ME.
I HAD NO IDEA.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
I WAS DRAWN INTO THE WORLD
OF DARKNESS JUST LIKE KEN.
KEN?
YOU'RE NOT LIKE KEN.
WE KEEP TOO MUCH INSIDE,
MAKING US VULNERABLE.
HELLO, HELLO.
RESCUE IS AT HAND.
GOING UP?
I'M GLAD THAT'S OVER.
UM...
KEN?
I'M SORRY, YOLEI.
I WASN'T ABLE TO HELP YOU.
THAT'S OKAY, KEN.
I KNOW YOU WERE AFRAID,
AND IT WOULD'VE BEEN SILLY
FOR YOU TO FALL DOWN WITH US.
YOU WERE SO FREAKED OUT,
YOU PROBABLY WOULDN'T
HAVE DONE ANY GOOD ANYWAY.
OH, RIGHT. I FORGOT.
YOU WERE THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
YOU WERE BRAVE BACK THEN.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HEY, YOLEI, STOP.
OOPS, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS YOU DON'T REALLY
WANT TO BE REMINDED OF THAT.
I WOULDN'T. HEY, GUESS WHAT
WE FOUND DOWN THERE.
YOU'LL THINK
THIS IS FUNNY.
IT WASN'T GATOMON'S
TAIL RING AT ALL.
IT WAS ONE
OF YOUR DARK RINGS.
OKAY,
THAT'S NOT FUNNY,
BUT I DIDN'T
MEAN FUNNY -- HA HA.
I MEANT FUNNY --
IRONIC FUNNY.
EVEN THOUGH YOU MADE THEM,
I'M NOT BLAMING YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT,
KARI? THIS IS SERIOUS.
I'M JUST
MAKING IT WORSE, HUH?
[ GASPS ]
KARI, WHAT'S WRONG?
THE WAVES --
I CAN HEAR THE WAVES.
KARI?
OH, NO.
OH, I KNEW IT.
IS THIS DARKNESS INSIDE OF ME --
INSIDE OF KEN? IS THAT WHY
WE CAN'T GET AWAY FROM IT?
I WISH I WERE STRONGER...
OR KNEW WHAT IT WANTED.
DON'T SCARE ME
LIKE THAT, KARI.
IT REALLY IS
THE DARK OCEAN.
OCEAN? ALL I SEE
ARE A BUNCH OF TREES.
IT IS INDEED
AN OCEAN OF TREES,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT'S WHAT THEY MEAN.
I ALMOST LOST KARI ONCE
BEFORE TO THIS STUPID OCEAN.
I WISH I KNEW
WHAT IT WANTS WITH HER.
KARI, YOU'VE BEEN HERE --
SEEN THIS BEFORE?
I DIDN'T KNOW ANYONE BUT ME
HAD EVER BEEN HERE.
KARI SEES IT
AND NOW KEN, TOO.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING!
WHOA.
YOLEI,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
SOMETHING DOESN'T
FEEL RIGHT HERE.
IT'S AS IF THE WORLD
HAS SLIPPED OUT OF PLACE.
I WONDER IF IT'S
BECAUSE THE POWERS
GUARDING THE DIGITAL WORLD
ARE LOSING THEIR GRIP.
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT
SOMETHING THAT IZZY TOLD US.
THIS COULD BE IMPORTANT.
WHAT POWERS
WAS HE TALKING ABOUT?
LOOK AT THAT, MUMMYMON.
ISN'T THIS DELIGHTFUL?
THOSE FOOLISH LITTLE CHILDREN
HAVE STUMBLED INTO A PHASE WARP.
THEY HAVE NO IDEA
HOW VULNERABLE THEY ARE.
IT'S SUCH A SHAME
WE HAVE TO KEEP FOLLOWING
BLACKWARGREYMON.
YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME.
THIS LITTLE OPERATION ISN'T
WORTHY OF MY PERSONAL ATTENTION.
SPIRAL NEEDLE!
ENJOY YOUR LUNCH,
MY DARLING.
[ GROWLS ]
I WANT TO GO HOME.
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT IT, KARI.
DON'T GIVE IN. I NEED YOU.
DON'T WORRY, KARI.
WE'LL BE HOME SOON, REMEMBER?
YOU SAID SO YOURSELF.
[ GROWLING ]
I THINK BIG BROTHER
IS WATCHING US.
OR AT LEAST HIS CORSAGE.
THAT'S BLOSSOMON --
AN ULTIMATE DIGIMON.
HER SPIRAL FLOWER ATTACK IS
A GOOD EXCUSE FOR WEED KILLER,
AND HER CHILDREN
ARE WORSE THAN THORNS.
HEY, BEHIND HER --
THERE'S A HOLE IN SPACE.
I CAN SEE
RIGHT THROUGH IT.
WHOA!
I BELIEVE THAT'S MY CUE.
ABOUT TIME. HE'LL HAVE
NO TROUBLE DIGIVOLVING NOW.
ARE YOU READY?
LET ME AT HER.
HAWKMON,
WORMMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
AQUILAMON, STINGMON!
IS IT OKAY?
MM-HMM.
OH!
AAH!
THIS IS NOT
A GOOD TIME.
BLAST RINGS!
NOT AGAIN.
DON'T TAKE ME!
I JUST DON'T THINK
I CAN STAND IT THIS TIME.
KARI,
SNAP OUT OF IT.
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT.
SPIKING STRIKE!
STINGMON!
GRAND HORN!
[ CRYING ]
KARI, YOU HAVE TO TALK TO ME
OR I CAN'T HELP.
THE DARKNESS
WON'T LEAVE ME ALONE.
I'LL NEVER BE STRONG ENOUGH.
IT'S GOING TO WIN.
THAT'S ENOUGH
OF THAT NONSENSE.
OF COURSE
YOU'RE STRONG ENOUGH.
YOU'RE THE STRONGEST PERSON
I'VE EVER KNOWN,
AND IF YOU THINK I'M GOING
TO LET YOU ROT ON YOURSELF,
YOU CAN THINK AGAIN.
WE'LL FIGHT IT TOGETHER,
KARI.
THE DARKNESS WILL NEVER
BEAT YOU, DO YOU HEAR ME?
YOLEI, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE A TRUE FRIEND.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
JUST LIKE YOU.
I FORGOT -- YOURS IS
THE CREST OF LIGHT.
YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO LIGHT UP THE DARKNESS.
IT DOESN'T HAVE
A CHANCE.
YOU'RE THE WORST ENEMY
OF DARKNESS.
YEAH.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
♪ DIGIMON ♪
AQUILAMON!
GATOMON!
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIVOLVE ♪
SILPHYMON!
Man: SILPHYMON
IS THE DNA DIGIVOLVE FORM
OF GATOMON AND AQUILAMON.
SILPHYMON'S STATIC FORCE
IS THE ULTIMATE WEAPON
AGAINST DARKNESS AND HATE.
IT HAS GATOMON'S GRACE.
AND AQUILAMON'S STRENGTH.
THAT OVERGROWN DAISY
IS HISTORY.
LET'S SEND THIS
CONTROL SPIRE DIGIMON
BACK TO THE SPIRE
IN A DUSTPAN.
I LIKE THE WAY
YOU THINK, GATOMON.
STATIC FORCE!
AAH!
♪ LET'S ALL GET DIGITAL ♪
LOOK OVER THERE!
I'LL BET IT'S THEM.
THEY STARTED WITHOUT US.
WOW.
DOUBLE WOW.
[ Both thinking ]
YOU KNOW, SHE'S PRETTY COOL.
Both: HUH?
Yolei: SALAMON.
I'M GARURUMON NOW,
YOLEI.
SILPHYMON, HUH?
OH, RATS.
I GUESS THAT MEANS YOLEI IS
KARI'S DNA DIGIVOLVE PARTNER.
TOO BAD, T.K.
YOU'RE ALL TOGETHER NOW.
TIME FOR ME TO GO.
KEN!
[ Thinking ]
THERE'S A LOT MORE TO KEN
THAN A PRETTY FACE,
AND KARI, TOO.
THEY FIGHT ENEMIES
I NEVER EVEN SEE.
SHE WON'T FIGHT THEM
ALONE ANYMORE.
I THOUGHT I'D REALLY
LOST YOU THIS TIME.
I WAS AFRAID YOU HAD SLIPPED
INTO THE OTHER WORLD FOR GOOD.
DON'T WORRY, T.K.
I HAVE A FEELING I WON'T
BE FIGHTING IT ALONE ANYMORE.
HMM?
YOLEI WON'T LET ME.
Man: HAVE KARI AND KEN
SEEN THE LAST OF THE DARK OCEAN?
WILL KARI'S LIGHT DEFEAT
THE APPROACHING DARKNESS?
FIND OUT ON
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."