We all made it back home in
one piece and without jet lag.
Good thing too because
Arukenimon and Mummymon
were busy while we were gone.
They kidnapped kids
from all over the city
and then strange Digimon
started popping up everywhere.
These Digimon weren't
just confused,
they were actually evil.
But they didn't seem
to be any happier
with Arukenimon than we were.
The older Digimon gave their
power to Imperialdramon
so he could Digiball
to his fighter mode.
But unfortunately,
he couldn't just
send SkullSatamon
back to the digital world
and he was attacking a
whole busload of kids.
Tai warned me this
day was coming.
(upbeat techno)
♪ Di Di Digi Digimon Digimon
♪ Di Di Di Digimon Digimon
♪ Di Di Di Digimon
Digital Monsters, Digimon
♪ are the Champions
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon are the Champions
♪ Change into Digital Champions
♪ to save the Digital World
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters,
Digimon are the Champions
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon are the Champions
♪ Digivolve into
Champions, Armor Digivolve
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters,
Digimon are the Champions
♪ Digimon are the Champions
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon!
Come back here, you
won't get away with this!
Bring back Ken or
I'm taking you down!
What a ghastly boy. Does he
really think he can catch us?
Stop you kidnappers!
I knew I should've done
those extra laps in P.E.
‐ Help's here. Jump in!
‐ Awesome.
So you're Joe's brother,
huh? But you're kinda cool.
‐ That's me.
‐ Poor Ken.
‐ Don't get bent
out of shape, pal.
Now that we've got these
cool wheels we'll catch 'em.
That's right. It's under
control, just trust us.
We made a deal, but
you double crossed me!
Sorry, it's a
bad habit of mine.
You promised to let
these kids go free!
Oh that?
Well it hardly seems
necessarily, don't you think?
Do you little twerps, I mean
kiddies, want to go home?
Mm‐mm?
Why not?
We're just dying to
know, are you Ken Ijijoji?
Yes, what about it?
I knew it. Wow, I've
heard all about you.
You're smart and
you rule at sports.
I bet you could do
just about anything
if you really wanted to.
It'd be awesome to be like that.
Then I met this
man and he told me
he knew a way I could do it.
What man?
[Man] (laughs) You
can't blame me can you?
After all it seems everyone
wants to be just like you.
Who's that?
It's me, of course.
[Ken] Me who?
What? I'm so insulted.
Don't tell me you don't remember
me. I'll give you a hint.
We were introduced at
your brother's funeral.
At my brother's funeral?
What are you saying?
You remember that.
Just think about it.
Mm‐Mm.
(ominous music)
Ha, I've seen your face!
Remember now?
I'm not sure.
(tires screeching)
(car horn blares)
Hey, Vandis?
What's the matter?
Can't you drive straight?
Egad! I'm blind as a bat.
Aren't you guys up late?
Don't be such fools, you know
you can never outrun Daemon.
(yelling)
That was some
crazy speed bump.
That was LadyDevimon.
Stop the car.
Let's get to work.
I have to ask you a favor.
Huh?
This is sort of embarrassing,
but here it goes,
I'm not trying to catnap but
I'm just not strong enough
to hold back LadyDevimon.
Would you mind giving
me a little boost?
I'd be more than
happy to oblige,
but it's up to you,
do you approve?
Just try to stop
her, that's all,
but be careful!
Do not destroy her.
(gasping)
You better make up your mind,
it's getting ugly out there.
Okay.
You don't have to
worry about a thing.
T. K. and I will be
there to back you up.
Be careful!
LadyDevimon needs
a lesson in manners.
I'm there.
[Male Digital Voice]: Digimon.
(whirring and upbeat techno)
Hawkmon digivolve to...
Aquilamon!
[Male Digital Voice] Digimon.
Gatomon!
DNA digivolve to Sylphimon!
♪ Digimon digital monsters
♪ Digimon!
‐ Woah.
My name is Oikawa Yukio.
I was a friend of your fathers.
[Ken] A friend?
We had what you'd call
a working relationship.
[Ken] I had no idea.
You were beside
yourself at the funeral,
so it's no surprise
you didn't notice me.
Maybe this'll spark your memory.
Your brother's end
was unfortunate,
but perhaps it was an
unlucky twist of fate.
Only he knows the truth.
(gasp)
It was you, you sent the e‐mail.
I always knew that
you were intelligent.
I was very concerned about you
and thought it
would be comforting.
Huh, And what
made you think that?
‐ Check it out.
‐ Right.
(grunts)
How annoying.
[Arukenimon] If you
could describe LadyDevimon,
what would you call her?
A pain.
Ken, these two are simply
assistants of mine.
Of course, they're both
very powerful themselves,
but if I sing their praises,
it goes straight to
their heads, right?
Yeah.
Enough games.
I want you to tell me
exactly who you are
and what it is you
want with me here.
Do you now?
Take it up a notch,
we're almost on their tail!
I'm a bit confused, first,
there was SkullSatamon,
and now, we're
fighting Lady Devimon.
Do you think there's
any connection
between them and Arukenimon?
Yeah, a bad connection.
Darkness Wave!
Static Force!
(truck screeching)
Those snots are too
pushy for their own good.
Hot dog! It's like
a movie car chase!
I don't think this
is what my dad had
in mind when he
loaned me his car.
(gasp)
We almost got him,
put it in overdrive.
Come on, floor it.
We'll beat those
turkeys to the punch.
(gasping)
(laughs)
(bells and sirens)
Come on, come on.
(grunting)
Cool it guys, don't
sweat it, we'll catch 'em.
We just have to wait
for the train to pass.
It's not that easy.
(grunting)
(bell ringing)
It's about time, come on, gate.
We still have
time to catch 'em.
Mm‐hmm.
Hope so.
(bell ringing)
‐ (siren blaring)
‐ (gasping)
(grunting)
[T. K.] What is this,
Grand Central Station?
Enough with the tricks already!
[Car Passengers] Give us
a break! Give us a break!
As soon as he
gets what we want,
we're out of here, got it?
Anything for you.
(grunts)
Why do you want me?
You must have some reason
for keeping me tied
up like a pretzel?
Ever since I first saw you,
I knew you had
something special.
A dark spirit deep inside.
If I planted the Dark Spore,
I knew that it would
be able to grow.
You're not making
a lot of sense.
What Dark Spore?
It's a magnificent device.
It makes a person smarter
and better at sports.
Well, that's powerful if
you really think about it.
These kids were excited
when I told them
what the Dark Spore had
to offer, right kids?
Hmm, they believed me and
want to be just like you,
so I had you brought here in
order to grant them their wish.
The Spore planted inside you
found fertile soil
in which to grow.
I'm going to borrow some of it
to implant in these children.
You have plenty.
You want my opinion?
You're as mad as they come.
Don't worry, I promise
you won't feel a thing.
All it is is some data
that will be transferred
electronically.
Just pretend you're
a box of cereal
and I'm scanning your bar code.
(electric zapping)
Hold still.
(grunts) Where's Davis or Mon?
(laughs)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(people screaming and yelling)
This is weird.
Let's go laser!
(laser beams)
(people screaming)
Alright, which one of you
kids would like to be next?
(grunts)
Well, I'm ready.
No, he's just trying to
trick you, can't you see that?
It's not like you
think it'll be.
You don't want to be like me.
[Mummymon] Wait, I
think I hear something,
can you hear it too?
No, is it Daemon?
The stars are
gossiping to each other.
Huh?
They're saying they know
a cute couple of Digimon
that would make
beautiful music together.
Perhaps they're trying
to tell us something.
What do you think?
Ugh, did you say
cute? I hate cute!
I think it's a sign!
Come on, give me a big
smooch and let's celebrate.
(hard blow and grunting)
Cram it, Bandage Breath!
I'm the guy for you, you
just don't know it yet.
The stars said so.
Let me give you some advice.
Give up star‐gazing and
don't be such a numskull.
Okay, why don't
you tell me what
it is you're looking
for and I'll be that.
You don't like cute,
you don't like stars.
Would you like a puppy?
Ugh, why don't you
become invisible?
Arukenimon.
(people screaming)
Come on, we've been on
scarier coasters before!
That's not what I'm
worried about, what's that?
Maybe it's a new ride?
(monster growling)
They have such a
high opinion of you.
It's just so
heart‐warming. (laughs)
(people screaming)
Stop right there!
Sorry folks, this road's closed
to all vehicles and pedestrians.
Is it a construction zone?
'Cause we have to get
through there now!
We've been tailing some
bad dudes driving a truck.
It's big like this,
did it pass here?
Look kid, we've got
a major catastrophe
in progress, now, move it!
(gasping)
Come on, let's go!
Right, huh?
What's wrong, huh?
[T. K.] What's that?
[Veemon] I'm afraid
it's MarineDevimon!
Hold 'em off while
I go after the truck!
You're up to bat Veemon!
(whooshing)
Digi‐Armor energize!
(whooshing and whirring)
[Male Digital Voice]
Digimon, Digimon.
[Veemon] Veemon
Armor Digivolve Tool!
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon are the champions
[Male Digital Voice]
Armor Digivolve.
♪ Digimon Digital Monsters
[Male] Raidramon,
the Storm of Friendship
♪ Digital Monsters
♪ Digimon!
(growls)
Jump on, Wormmon, now!
(grunting and screaming)
[Policeman] Everybody,
just stay calm!
Let's make salmon patties
out of that big oaf.
Are you saying we
should destroy him?
T. K., you sure
about that? (gasps)
(monster growling)
(building crashing)
[Female] Honey, our home!
(gasps)
(grunts and crashes)
Okay.
Armadillomon
digivolve to...
Ankylomon!
Patamon digivolve to...
Angemon!
Ankylomon!
[both] DNA digivolve
to Shakkouman!
(police sirens)
That doesn't sound good.
(grunts) Can you get a look?
Yeah, she's still going at it.
[Yolei] Well, that's
good news, who's winning?
Um, can't tell.
Static Force!
Darkness Wave!
(bats chirping and fluttering)
(screams)
What's the matter, got
bats in your belfry? (laughs)
Hold on!
(dramatic orchestral music)
Kachina Bombs!
(grunts)
Don't get me mad, I don't
want to have to hurt you.
(electric shocks)
Go Shakkoumon!
That's the way,
we're counting on you!
You're the only one that
can stop MarineDevimon!
(crashes)
(gasping)
[Man] He must've come
from a costume party.
[Man with Blue Hat]
Hey, you okay?
I'm fine (grunts),
but get me outta here.
How humiliating!
Wow, I bet she was at
the costume party too
and won first prize.
[Man with Blue Hat] Sweet.
[Silphymon] Watch
it, she's dangerous!
I don't get it, dude!
(LadyDevimon laughs)
She's too pretty.
Stay away!
This is convenient, do
you like being my shield?
(grunts)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(monster grunting)
(tires screeching)
[Wormmon] Where do you
think they're taking him?
I gotta pretty good idea.
Where?
It's nearby.
What's it called?
Heightened View Terrace,
that's the place where Kari
and Tai first got a
look at a Digimon.
They say that it's an
entry to the Digital World.
Oh no, do you think Arukenimon
and the others know about it?
[Oikawa] I think
Heightened View Terrace
is much to cheery of a name.
Hmm?
Huh, I say they rename it
Dark View Terrace instead.
That's much more appropriate.
I'm surprised, I thought
you'd appreciate my humor.
I suppose you think you're
a superior human being.
Well, you should
think again. (laughs)
The face of disdain, look how
he turns his nose up at us.
You can learn something
from all this, kids.
This is an example of
how your exalted hero
gives the cold shoulder to
those less worthy than himself.
(laughs)
(sighs)
(zapping)
(grunts)
(laughs and grunts)
What you waiting for?
A written invitation, come on!
Give me your best shot!
Hey, wait, whatever I
did, I didn't mean it.
Well, if you're just
going to sit there,
I'll go home and file
my fangs, so bye‐bye.
No! (grunts)
(smashes)
[Kari] Yolei!
Stop that! What's
the matter with you!
He's just an innocent kid!
That's called fighting
dirty, coward!
Watch it, Yolei! Be careful!
You think I'm a coward?
You humans are so pathetic
with your honor and
your compassion.
I'll show you honor.
I'll win!
(Yolei gasps)
You won't stand in my way.
No, Yolei! (screams)
You asked for it!
(Kari and Yolei scream)
Huh? Oh no.
You have to understand,
I didn't have a choice.
You were in great danger.
You vaporized her.
She's finished.
I made a mistake.
[Man] Dude, are you okay?
[Man with Blue Hat] Oh man,
what just happened there?
(men conversing)
It was the right thing to do.
You saved that guy's life.
Oh.
‐ Hmm.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(people screaming)
This is bad.
The patients inside are
going to need some help.
We've got to get in there.
Please, Shakkouman,
move away from here.
(people screaming)
(Shakkouman grunting)
We have to do something
before someone gets hurt.
Let's go.
There's no sense wasting
more time just sitting here.
I actually gave up
a medical career.
Who'd believe I'm here
doing what I'm doing.
This just proves you
don't have to be a doctor
to make an important
difference and save lives.
Yeah.
[Cody Voiceover] My dad was
a police officer.
He saved lots of lives too.
I bet he'd be really
proud if he saw me now.
(wailing)
[Cody] Shakkoumon!
Justice Beam!
(whirring)
He's completely gone.
You destroyed it, Digimon.
You really destroyed him.
[Doctor] Thank you so
much for all your help.
I don't know what
we would have done
if you hadn't come along.
Thanks a lot.
Come on, Ace. Let's go.
Oh, yeah.
Bye.
[Cody Voiceover] It seemed
like the right thing
to do at the time,
Dad, but I don't know.
I just hope it really was.
(tires screeching)
Isn't that kid
getting saddle sore yet?
Speed up, Raidramon.
You can do it!
Right!
You think you're so smart.
How'd you like
to do the rumba?
(tires screeching)
Don't worry, you two.
I'm not going anywhere.
Just hold on tight.
You are completely useless.
(gasps)
Huh?
(whirring)
‐ Who's that guy?
‐ Don't ask me.
[Narrator] Who is Daemon?
Will the Dark Spore
grow and spread?
Find out in the next episode
of Digimon: Digital Monsters.
(kids laughing)
(playful tune)
(upbeat techno)