Yoli: MIMI WAS VISITING
FROM AMERICA.
SHE'S SO GLAMOROUS.
WE ALL DECIDED
TO SPEND SATURDAY
PICNICKING
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
SOME OF US GOT SEPARATED
AND FELL INTO A NEW AREA
THAT WAS CONTROLLED
BY A CONTROL SPIRE.
THAT'S WHY THE GEKKOMON
DIDN'T REMEMBER MIMI.
PAOMON REMEMBERED HER
AND SAVED US FROM THEM.
THEY WERE HAPPY
TO SEE EACH OTHER,
BUT WE WEREN'T HAPPY
TO SEE THE ROACHMON BROTHERS.
WE MADE THEM DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE FOR US.
I WISH MIMI WERE STAYING.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE SISTERS.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Nefertimon: ROSETTA STONE!
YEAH!
Izzy: ALL RIGHT! THAT'S 12 MORE
CONTROL SPIRES DESTROYED!
YEAH!
ACCORDING TO THE MAP,
GREYMON IS FINISHED
IN THIS AREA
AND IS MOVING ON
TO THE NEXT.
GARURUMON IS DOING
THE SAME THING!
THERE'S STILL ONE MORE
CONTROL SPIRE TO DESTROY TODAY.
Matt: MAYBE GREYMON
CAN GET THAT ONE, TOO.
I DON'T THINK HE CAN.
HE'S TOO FAR FROM THAT AREA.
TAI'S RIGHT.
IN THAT CASE,
WE'LL DO IT OURSELVES.
INTRUDER! INTRUDER!
I AM GUARDROMON.
WHOEVER TRIES
TO ENTER THE PREMISES
SHALL BECOME VICTIMS
OF MY GRENADE DESTROYER ATTACK.
GOLD RUSH!
STAR SHOWER!
FIRE ROCKET!
INTRUDER! INTRUDER!
THERE MUST 100 OF THEM!
YOU COUNTED THAT HIGH
WITHOUT EVEN TAKING OFF
YOUR SHOES AND SOCKS!
T.K.: NOW IS A GOOD TIME
TO GO BACK TO OUR WORLD.
WE CAN COME UP
WITH A NEW PLAN.
Kari: T.K.'s RIGHT.
WE CAN TALK TO IZZY.
ARE YOU GUYS
OUT OF YOUR MINDS?
QUIT NOW?
I'VE NEVER BEEN A QUITTER.
I AGREE.
DAVIS, LET'S REGROUP.
DAVIS, DON'T BE SO STUBBORN.
THERE ARE FAR TOO MANY
OF THEM.
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
Kari: I AGREE.
WE HAVE TO HURRY.
OH, ALL RIGHT...
HEAD FOR THE GATE!
Yoli: DIGIPORT, OPEN!
[ PANTING ]
HELP!
GRENADE DESTROYER!
Kari: WAIT FOR ME!
All: AAH!
SAY, SHOULDN'T WE PUT
PILLOWS HERE
IF WE'RE GOING
TO KEEP DOING THIS?
THE TV WAS BLOWN UP
AS WE CAME THROUGH,
SO WE CAN'T GO BACK.
WHERE DID KARI GO?
SHE'S TRAPPED
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD!
I'LL SEND THE OTHERS A MESSAGE
SAYING WE'RE OKAY.
I DON'T THINK
THIS HAS SPELL CHECK.
KARI, IF WE FIND OURSELVES
IN ANY KIND OF JAM,
I CAN ALWAYS ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
WELL, LET'S SAVE THAT
FOR A SPECIAL OCCASION.
Yoli: THE GATE IS CLOSED.
WE CAN'T GET TO HER.
T.K.,
WASN'T KARI BEHIND YOU
WHEN YOU WENT INTO THE GATE
FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD?
MM-HMM.
WHY DIDN'T YOU LET HER
GO FIRST?
IT WAS NO ONE'S FAULT.
IT JUST HAPPENS.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
I STILL KNOW WHEN SOMEONE'S
BEING A JERK.
OH, I GUESS THAT'S ME.
THE TRUTH IS,
DAVIS IS RIGHT.
HUH?
IT REALLY WAS MY FAULT.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN WATCHING OUT
FOR HER ALL ALONG.
WELL, I GUESS
I COULD'VE, TOO.
SO COULD I.
Cody: THAT'S WHAT I MEAN.
THERE'S NO ONE TO BLAME.
HUH?
HEY, GUYS,
IT'S AN E-MAIL FROM KARI.
HUH?
IT SAYS, "I'M ALL RIGHT.
I'M SORRY IF ANY WORDS ARE
MISSPELLED. SINCERELY, KARI."
YOLI, I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
IF I CAN FIND AN AREA
CLOSE TO THE ONE SHE'S IN,
THEN I CAN REACH HER.
GOT IT!
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
I'M GOING, TOO!
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
IF HE THINKS I'M GOING
TO STAND BY
AND LET HIM BE THE HERO,
HE CAN FORGET IT!
WHAT? THEN I'M GOING.
YOLI, WAIT A MINUTE.
IT'S ALMOST DINNERTIME.
THEIR FAMILIES ARE GOING
TO WONDER WHERE THEY ARE.
WE HAVE TO TELL TAI
AND THE OTHERS.
I THINK THAT'S THE BEST THING
YOU AND I CAN DO
TO HELP DAVIS AND T.K.
RIGHT NOW.
CODY, I KNOW
YOU'RE JUST A KID,
BUT SOMETIMES YOU HAVE
THE WISDOM OF AN OLD MAN OF 20.
BUT WAIT! YOU CAN'T
JUST GO OUT IN PUBLIC!
Davis: [ Sarcastically ]
THIS WAS A GREAT IDEA,
CROSSING THE DESERT
WITHOUT ANY WATER.
THERE'S THE CITY!
LOOKS LIKE ONE
OF THOSE THINGS YOU SHAKE
AND IT STARTS SNOWING.
I'LL GET KARI. WAIT HERE.
NO, I'LL GET KARI.
YOU WAIT HERE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WE'LL FLIP FOR IT.
WINNER GOES.
LOSER STAYS HERE.
SINCE IT'S MY COIN,
I GET TO CALL IT. TAILS.
OKAY, IF IT'S TAILS,
I RESCUE KARI.
IF IT'S HEADS,
YOU GET TO GO.
TAILS!
I'LL TELL HER THAT
YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT HER
AND THAT YOU WERE -- AAH!
A COIN THAT HAS TAILS
ON BOTH SIDES.
THAT'S HOW I USED
TO BEAT MATT.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
LET'S BOTH GO.
OKAY, T.M.
DID YOU REALLY USE ONE
OF THOSE COINS ON MATT?
YEAH, THAT'S HOW I GOT
ALL MY BASEBALL CARDS
AND HIS OLD GUITAR.
T.K. AND DAVIS
SURE ARGUE A LOT. HOW COME?
SOMETHING ABOUT KARI.
HUMAN GIRLS MAKE HUMAN BOYS
ACT SORT OF WEIRD.
INTRUDER! INTRUDER!
INTRUDER!
ROSETTA STONE!
KARI, THERE AREN'T
ANY TVs LEFT IN THIS AREA.
WE'LL HAVE TO GO
TO ANOTHER AREA TO FIND ONE.
BUT WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHICH DIRECTION TO TRAVEL.
HA HA HA HA!
IT'S ALMOST YOUR DINNERTIME.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
GOING HOME SOON, KEN?
NEVER CALL ME ANYTHING
BUT MASTER!
[ WHIMPERING ]
SINCE SHE'S ALL ALONE,
SHE DESERVES SOMEONE SPECIAL.
OH, NO, YOU CAN'T.
ANYONE BUT HIM.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
HELLO, CAN I SPEAK
TO TAI, PLEASE?
NO, I'M NOT
SELLING ANYTHING.
YOLI, WITH ALL THE SNACKS
AND DRINKS YOU TAKE,
IT'S A WONDER THIS STORE
SHOWS ANY PROFIT AT ALL.
PUT IT ON MY TAB,
DADDY.
SO THAT'S
WHERE KARI IS NOW, TAI.
OKAY, CODY,
THANKS FOR LETTING ME KNOW.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
KARI'S AT A FRIEND'S HOUSE
DOING A SCIENCE PROJECT
ON GRAVITY,
AND THEY NEED TO SEE HOW LONG
I CAN STAND ON MY HEAD.
TAI, I HEARD.
SO ARE YOU GOING TO GO?
IN A FEW MINUTES,
BUT FIRST I HAVE TO STOP
BY DAVIS' APARTMENT.
I HAVE TO TELL HIS FAMILY
THAT HE'S GOING
TO BE A LITTLE LATE TONIGHT.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF IT.
YOU GO ON AND GET TO KARI.
RIGHT. THANKS, MATT.
OH, I FORGOT!
I LEFT MIMI ON HOLD
WHEN SHE CALLED FROM NEW YORK!
HER PHONE BILL!
I TOLD MY MOM WE WERE WORKING
ON A RESCUE PROJECT.
SHE SAID SHE'S GLAD
WE'RE HELPING STRAY CATS.
MY DAD WAS JUST GLAD
THAT I LEFT
WITHOUT FILLING UP
ANOTHER BAG.
THERE'S JUST ONE GUARD
AT THE DOOR.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TAKE HIM OUT.
OTHERWISE, HE'LL CALL
FOR REINFORCEMENTS.
Davis: NOT A PROBLEM.
V-MON AND I CAN HANDLE
THAT METAL HEAD.
V-MON, ARE YOU READY?
YEAH, LET'S DO IT!
WAIT A MINUTE!
I'LL DO IT.
THERE AREN'T ANY CONTROL SPIRES
IN THIS AREA, RIGHT?
WELL, JUST THE ONE
INSIDE THE DOME.
BUT WE'RE OUTSIDE.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT MEANS YOU CAN DIGEVOLVE!
HUH?
THEN GO FOR IT!
ALL RIGHT!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGEVOLVE INTO ULTIMATE!
PATAMON, DIGEVOLVE TO...
ANGEMON!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ANGEMON, I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN A WHILE.
AN-AN-ANGEMON?
HI THERE, BIG GUY.
INTRUDER!
ANGEL ROD!
INTRUDER...
[ SHUTS DOWN ]
I NAILED HIM.
YOU KNOW, THOSE CONTROL SPIRES
REALLY RUIN MY DAY.
T.K.: YOU DID GREAT,
PATAMON.
SO BESIDES
ARMOR DIGEVOLVING,
PATAMON CAN DIGEVOLVE
TO ANGEMON?
WHAT ABOUT GATOMON?
WELL, SHE CAN DIGEVOLVE
TO ANGEWOMON.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
ANGEMON AND ANGEWOMON?
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE MAKE A GREAT TEAM.
ONE QUESTION -- IS THERE
AN ANGEBABYMON, TOO?
SOMETIMES, HE SAYS
THE WEIRDEST THINGS.
HA HA HA.
V-MON!
HUH?
TELL ME RIGHT NOW
IF YOU CAN DIGEVOLVE
INTO ANGE-SOMETHING, TOO.
ANGE-DINOSAURMON,
ANGE-SOCCERPLAYERMON...
I JUST DON'T HAVE IT
IN ME!
HE'S STILL GOT A LOT
TO LEARN.
SO, ANYWAY, DAVIS IS OVER
AT MY BROTHER'S HOUSE,
AND SO HE PROBABLY WON'T
BE HOME UNTIL LATER ON.
[ GIGGLES ]
WHAT?
YOU'RE LYING.
I CAN TELL WHEN PEOPLE
ARE LYING
BECAUSE THEY USUALLY
START BLINKING A LOT.
[ Stuttering ]
WHAT...BUT...
I PROMISE NOT TO TELL
MY PARENTS YOU WERE LYING
IF YOU PROMISE TO GO OUT
ON A DATE WITH ME, OKAY?
SEE YOU FRIDAY AT 8:00.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
[ GROANS ]
HOW COME HE GETS
MORE CANDY THAN I DO?
STOP COMPLAINING.
THERE'S PLENTY MORE.
I BROUGHT
SOME REINFORCEMENTS.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
You summoned me,
your highness?
PLEASE HOLD
FOR THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
LINE ONE FOR YOU, SIR.
HEH HEH HEH HEH.
Both: DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
V-MON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
PATAMON,
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
PEGASUSMON --
FLYING HOPE!
FIRE ROCKET!
DAVIS, OVER HERE!
I CAN'T JUMP
AS HIGH AS YOU CAN!
I'M GETTING KARI'S SIGNAL!
WE'RE CLOSE!
YOU READY
TO JUMP A LITTLE HIGHER?
♪ HEY, IT REALLY
DOESN'T MATTER WHAT YOU TRY ♪
♪ IT'S GETTING EVEN HARDER
TO DENY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE REALITY HAS JUST
SAID GOODBYE ♪
Kari: BOY,
AM I GLAD TO SEE YOU!
GRENADE DESTROYER!
♪ IT'S GETTING HARDER
TO WIN ♪
♪ IT'S GETTING DIGITAL LAND ♪
♪ IT STARTS HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN ♪
INTRUDER! DESTROY!
[ HISSES ]
EQUUS BEAM!
FIRE ROCKET!
HEY, DAVIS, T.K.!
YOU GUYS ARE MY HEROES!
ACTUALLY,
IT WAS MOSTLY MY IDEA,
BUT I DECIDED TO BRING T.K.
ALONG FOR THE RIDE.
WHATEVER. HUH?
♪ IT'S GETTING DIGITAL LAND ♪
STAR SHOWER!
♪ IT STARTS HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN ♪
COME ON, KARI,
WE BETTER GET GOING.
HUH?
WHY CAN'T THESE GUYS
EVER BE SMALL?
ANDROMON!
I AM ANDROMON.
I HAVE ONE MISSION --
SEEK OUT MY ENEMY
AND DESTROY HIM
WITH MY LIGHTNING BLADE!
HUH? HE'S GOT A DARK RING.
ANDROMON?
I AM PROGRAMMED
TO DESTROY THE ENEMY.
YOU ARE THE ENEMY.
I WILL DESTROY YOU.
ANDROMON,
DON'T YOU REMEMBER US?
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS.
KARI, YOU'RE HANGING AROUND
WITH THE WRONG PEOPLE.
FLAMEDRAMON, YOU'LL HAVE
TO USE ALL YOUR POWER!
YOU'VE GOT IT!
FLAMING FIST!
LIGHTNING BLADE!
Both: [ GASP ]
V-MON, SPEAK TO ME.
YOU'RE KNEELING
ON MY TAIL.
STAR SHOWER!
LIGHTNING BLADE!
AAH!
I'LL HAVE TWO CHEESEBURGERS
AND A LARGE ORDER OF FRIES.
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
SO WHAT NOW?
ANDROMON, DON'T YOU REMEMBER
HOW WE FOUGHT TOGETHER
SIDE BY SIDE?
KARI, WE HAVE
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF IT'S THE SAME ANDROMON.
EVEN IF IT IS,
HE'S UNDER THE CONTROL
OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
HE CAN'T EVEN HEAR
YOUR VOICE.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
AS MUCH
AS I LIKE YOU TWO ARGUING,
HE'S HEADING RIGHT FOR US!
LET'S GO!
YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
HERE COMES HELP NOW!
I'M GLAD
WE'RE NOT TOO LATE.
HI, GUYS!
I THOUGHT,
SINCE I WAS HERE,
I'D BUILD THIS CITY
A SUBWAY SYSTEM!
HOLD STILL,
YOU PILE OF SCRAP METAL!
GOLD RUSH!
HUH? HEY, THAT COMMENT ABOUT
SCRAP METAL WAS JUST A JOKE.
Tai: KARI, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, BUT, TAI,
IT'S ANDROMON!
ANDROMON, SLOW DOWN!
IT'S ME -- TAI.
TAI WHO?
Andromon: OH, TAI!
WHOA!
KARI, LOOK OUT!
All: [ GASP ]
HEY, YOU PUT HER DOWN NOW!
DO YOU REMEMBER ME?
I AM...TRYING.
YES.
WE ALL TOOK A PICTURE
TOGETHER.
A PICTURE?
Andromon: FACES...
LONG AGO.
DIGIDESTINED...
I LOVE JIGSAW PUZZLES.
NOW I SEE THE COMPLETE PICTURE.
KARI,
I'M SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE
I'VE CAUSED.
ANDROMON!
MM-HMM!
THAT CONTROL SPIRE
IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL THIS.
WELL, NO MORE.
GATLING ATTACK!
Kari: ANDROMON,
ARE ALL OF THESE GUARDROMON
GOING TO STAY BROKEN
FOREVER?
NO, THEIR PROGRAMS
WERE REWRITTEN
BY THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
THEY JUST NEED
TO BE REPROGRAMMED. WATCH.
ACTUALLY, ONCE I REPROGRAM
THE GUARDROMON,
I'LL STAY HERE
TO PROTECT THEM
IN CASE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR RETURNS.
I FEEL FRESH AS A DAISY.
Tai: COME ON, GUYS,
LET'S GO HOME.
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH-AY-OH ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
IZZY, WERE YOU WAITING
THIS WHOLE TIME?
SHH. LET'S GO.
MATT JUST CALLED AND TOLD ME
WHAT HAD HAPPENED WITH KARI,
AND I'M REALLY UPSET YOU GUYS
HAVE LEFT ME OUT OF THE LOOP.
CODY CALLED TAI FOR HELP,
AND TAI CALLED MATT.
NO ONE CALLS ME
UNTIL THE ADVENTURE IS OVER.
THERE WAS JUST NO TIME
TO CALL YOU.
YOU'RE A BIG PART
OF THE TEAM.
THAT'S RIGHT,
AND AS A TEAM MEMBER,
I EXPECT TO BE TREATED
WITH THE SAME RESPECT
I GIVE TO ALL OF YOU.
I'VE GOTTEN US OUT OF JAMS
WITH MY PARTICULAR SKILLS.
I'M SORRY
I DIDN'T CALL YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL RESPECT.
OKAY, I FORGIVE YOU.
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT
THE REASON I CAME HERE.
I EXAMINED THE NEW DIGIVICES
AND DETERMINED THAT THEY HAVE
THREE DIFFERENT SETTINGS --
DIGITAL, DETECT,
AND DISCOVER.
MAYBE WE SHOULD CALL THEM
D-3s FROM NOW ON.
PRODIGIOUS LITTLE DEVICES,
AREN'T THEY?
I HAD HELP WITH THE RESEARCH
FROM MY FRIEND WALLACE
IN AMERICA.
MAYBE YOU GUYS
WILL MEET HIM SOMEDAY.
THE D-3s
MIGHT HAVE SENT A MESSAGE
TO ANDROMON'S MEMORY BANKS,
WHICH THEN -- AAH!
PLEASE FINISH TALKING
AFTER WE EAT.
WE FORGOT ABOUT DINNER.
THAT'S RIGHT. OUR PARENTS
ARE WAITING FOR US.
THE FOOD'S PROBABLY COLD
AND SOGGY BY NOW.
OF COURSE, FOR MY MOM,
THAT'S AN IMPROVEMENT.
SOME GIRL NAMED JUN
CALLED TODAY, MATT,
AND SHE SAID YOU HAVE A DATE
WITH HER ON FRIDAY.
SHE MADE DINNER RESERVATIONS
FOR YOU TWO AT O'MALLEY'S.
AT O'MALLEY'S?
WHAT'S THAT?
THE MOST EXPENSIVE
RESTAURANT IN TOWN.
[ Thinking ]
THIS IS ALL DAVIS' FAULT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I HAVE TO TAKE HIS SISTER
OUT ON A DATE.
HEY, MATT,
SOMETHING SMELLS GREAT.
DINNER'S READY?
SUPPERTIME!
KEN, DEAR, YOU'RE BUSY.
I'LL LEAVE IT
OUTSIDE YOUR DOOR.
BLAST! THOSE DIGIVICES
ARE BECOMING A NUISANCE TO ME!
I'VE GOT TO GET THEM AWAY
FROM THOSE KIDS!
Man: WHAT IS
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S PLOT
AGAINST THE DIGIDESTINED?
FIND OUT NEXT TIME ON
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."