Cody: THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
WAS NOT ONLY HUNTING DIGIMON,
BUT HE WAS ALSO MAKING THEM
FIGHT EACH OTHER.
WE DETECTED MORE DIGIEGGS,
BUT A GANG OF TYRANOMON
ATTACKED US UNDER ORDERS
FROM THE EMPEROR,
SO WE SPLIT UP.
T.K. AND KARI FOUND THEIR
DIGIEGGS INSIDE OF A CAVE.
GATOMON WAS ABLE
TO ARMOR DIGEVOLVE
INTO NEFERTIMON,
AND PATAMON TRANSFORMED
INTO PEGASUSMON,
AND WITH THEIR HELP,
WE DEFEATED THE TYRANOMON
AND BROKE THEM FREE
FROM THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
DARK RINGS.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PATA BREATH, POI!
V-HEAD BUTT!
COME ON! LET'S ROCK!
ALWAYS EASY.
[ GROWLING ]
YOU GUYS ARE
OFFICIALLY FUGITIVES.
IF THAT'S THE DEFENSE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S GOING
TO PUT UP,
THIS FIGHT WILL BE OVER
IN THE FIRST ROUND.
SOMETHING WAS WEIRD.
IT WAS SO EASY FOR US
TO BREAK OUT OF THAT PRISON.
IT'S LIKE HE WANTED US
TO DO IT.
I THINK
HE'S UP TO SOMETHING.
HE TOOK ONE LOOK
AT OUR AWESOME SKILLS
AND HIT THE ROAD.
ACTUALLY, DAVIS, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO AGREE WITH T.K.
THIS GUY IS NOT GOING
TO LET US GET AWAY EASY
WITHOUT SOME REASON.
WORRY LATER. LET'S GET BACK
TO THE REAL WORLD.
I'M STARVING. I CAN PRACTICALLY
SMELL THE CAFETERIA FROM HERE.
Davis: THAT'S MY PEANUT BUTTER
AND JELLY BEAN SANDWICH
I'VE HAD IN MY POCKET
SINCE LAST WEEK.
WHAT'S THAT TOWER?
THE NEXT ONE SHOULD BE
IN PLACE RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
THERE! NOW TO LET EVERYONE
KNOW WHO'S THE BOSS.
THIS CONTROL SPIRE
IS THE MOST DOMINATING OBJECT
IN THE DIGIWORLD.
WHEREVER I BUILD ONE,
THAT AREA WILL BE
UNDER MY CONTROL.
IT'S USELESS
TO TRY AND ESCAPE.
THOSE WHO DO WILL HAVE
TO ANSWER TO MY SOLDIERS.
[ Thinking ] HOW DO I GET
MYSELF INTO THESE THINGS?
AAH!
ARE YOU CRAZY, BRINGING
THE GATSUMON BACK
FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD?
WE COULDN'T JUST
LEAVE THEM THERE
FOR THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
TO MAKE INTO SLAVES, RIGHT?
HOW ARE WE GOING
TO EXPLAIN IT
IF MR. FUJIYAMA HAPPENS
TO COME IN HERE?
I'LL TELL HIM I'M TAKING
A SCULPTING CLASS,
AND THESE ARE SOME
OF MY EARLY MASTERPIECES.
Yoli: EARLY REJECTS
MIGHT BE A BETTER PHRASE.
HA HA.
YOLI, WOULD IT BE
ALL RIGHT WITH YOU
IF I BORROWED YOUR DIGIVICE?
BUT WHAT FOR?
THE POWER FROM YOUR DIGIVICES
OPENS THE GATE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
OUR OWN DIGIVICES
DON'T SEEM TO WORK.
I'VE TRIED USING MINE,
BUT NO LUCK.
THE ONLY WAY IS IF ONE OF YOU
OPENS THE GATE FOR US.
I WANTED TO TRY AN EXPERIMENT
WITH THE NEW DIGIVICES
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
MM-HMM.
LET'S MOVE OUT.
I'VE GOT AN EARLY TEE TIME
IN THE MORNING.
[ DIGIMON GROWLING ]
OH, WHY WAIT?
EVERYONE, STAY TO THE BACK
OF THE CELL.
BLUE BLASTER!
OH!
UNH!
APPARENTLY, YOU DON'T LISTEN
TO INSTRUCTIONS!
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M THE DIGIWORLD'S BIGGEST
SALAD BAR -- RED VEGIMON!
I AM THE BIGGEST
AND THE RIPEST OF ALL VEGIMON.
MY STINK-GEN ATTACK DESTROYS
MY ENEMIES WITH NOXIOUS FUMES!
TRY TO STOP US, STINKY.
FOR TRYING TO ESCAPE,
YOU GET TO SMELL MY ROOTS!
AND I HAVE ROOT ROT!
SMELL THIS!
SMELL IT AGAIN!
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
NO MORE, PLEASE!
YOU KIDDING?
I'M JUST WARMING UP!
[ GROANS ]
HEY, IF YOU CAN'T STAND
THE SMELL,
THEN GET OUT
OF THE KITCHEN!
AAH!
MY FUR IS DRY CLEAN ONLY!
LET THAT BE A LESSON
TO ALL OF YOU.
DON'T TRY TO DEFY THE POWER
OF THE DIGIMON EMPEROR!
[ GROANING ]
I'VE GOT
TO TELL THE OTHERS.
THEY NEED TO BE WARNED.
I HAVE TO FIND MATT.
OH...
MAN, I STINK.
[ PLAYING ROCK MUSIC ]
LISTEN, T.K., JUST BECAUSE
I HAVE A ROCK BAND
DOESN'T MEAN I CAN HIDE
A BAND OF ROCKS
THAT HAPPEN TO BE DIGIMON.
MAYBE THEY CAN BE
YOUR BACKUP SINGERS.
OH! CAN I HAVE
YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
SURE. WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
JUST MAKE IT
TO JUN MOTOMIYA.
DID YOU SAY "MOTOMIYA"?
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO BE
DAVIS' SISTER, WOULD YOU?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WHO ARE YOU?
HIS NAME'S T.K.
HE'S MY LITTLE BROTHER.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
DAVIS AND I ARE
IN THE SAME CLASS TOGETHER.
WILL YOU SIGN
MY SHIRT, TOO?
I GET ALL THE CUTE BOYS
TO SIGN IT.
I HAVEN'T WASHED
THIS SHIRT IN TWO YEARS.
NOT A LOT OF ROOM.
I THINK ALL BOYS
ARE CUTE.
THERE'S SOME KIND OF TROUBLE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I JUST GOT AN E-MAIL.
IT'S FROM YOLI.
IT SAYS, "EMERGENCY!
HURRY BACK TO SCHOOL."
EMERGENCY?
I HOPE GABUMON'S OKAY.
Yoli: BACK OFF, DAVIS!
YOU'RE MAKING ME NERVOUS.
CAN'T YOU GO ANY FASTER?
ALL RIGHT,
THE GATE'S OPEN.
SHALL WE GO?
Matt: GABUMON!
[ Groans ] OH, MATT...
GABUMON, ARE YOU OKAY?
LET'S JUST SAY
I'LL NEVER LOOK
AT STEAMED VEGETABLES
THE SAME WAY.
TELL ME EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED.
GOOD. WE NEVER TALK
ANYMORE.
I'm going over to Izzy's
to get my digivice back,
and then I'll meet up
with you there.
Have no fear
while Yoli's gone.
This place shall
be guarded by Boromon.
WHY DO THEY CALL
THOSE THINGS
ON TOP OF THE TV
RABBIT EARS?
WHY DON'T THEY
CALL THEM CAT EARS?
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU SAW A RABBIT
SLEEPING ON TOP
OF A TV?
OKAY, BREAK'S OVER.
LET'S GET BACK TO WORK.
IT'S A SMALL VILLAGE
CALLED SANTA CARILLA.
Davis: SOUNDS LIKE
IT'S IN CALIFORNIA.
IT WAS ALWAYS
A QUIET PLACE.
EVERYONE MINDED
THEIR OWN BUSINESS,
AND THEN THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
CAME ALONG.
THERE'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS
THAT SCARED THE GATSUMON.
THE EMPEROR CALLS THEM
CONTROL SPIRES.
LET'S GO!
WE CAN'T JUST RUSH IN THERE.
FOR ALL YOU KNOW, HE'S
IN THERE WAITING FOR US,
AND THIS IS SOME KIND
OF AMBUSH.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
HE MIGHT BE USING
DIGIMON HOSTAGES
AS A SHIELD
TO PROTECT HIMSELF.
WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO RESCUE THE HOSTAGES
AND MAKE SURE THAT NONE
OF THEM GET HURT.
THEY'RE BEING GUARDED
BY THE VEGIMON.
WATCH OUT
FOR THE DIGISLUDGE!
PATAMON, TELL US EVERYTHING
ABOUT RED VEGIMON.
OKAY.
WE'RE NOT NEEDED
AROUND HERE.
LET'S GO OFF
AND DO THINGS OUR OWN WAY.
I THINK WE SHOULD
ALL STICK TOGETHER.
OH!
I'VE GOT A PLAN TO SNEAK
INTO THE PRISON.
WAIT A MINUTE!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
WE CAN'T TAKE THE CHANCE THAT
ANY OF US, ESPECIALLY KARI,
MIGHT BE ATTACKED
WITH THAT DIGISLUDGE.
WE'VE BEEN ATTACKED BY A LOT
WORSE THINGS THAN DIGISLUDGE.
YEAH.
I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE
YOU'RE NOT WORRIED
ABOUT KARI'S WELL-BEING, T.A.
T.A.?
HE FORGOT HOW TO SPELL T.K.
HA HA HA HA.
[ GROANS ]
STOP RIGHT THERE!
IDENTIFY YOURSELVES!
IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE ONE OF YOU.
WE JUST CAPTURED THESE DIGIMON
AND THEIR FRIENDS.
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING US?
PIPE DOWN. YOU'RE ALL GOING
TO JAIL WHERE YOU BELONG.
HA HA HA!
MOVE IT, MOVE IT, MOVE IT!
THOSE GUYS DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE
THESE RINGS ARE PLASTIC.
THE FIRST SET OF GUARDS
WERE JUST FLUNKIES.
WE HAVEN'T FACED
THE PICK OF THE LITTER,
AND IF WE GET PAST THEM,
WE STILL HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO DESTROY THE CONTROL SPIRE.
THANKS FOR BRINGING
THE PRISONERS IN.
THE EMPEROR WILL BE PLEASED.
WE COULD'VE CAUGHT THEM,
BUT I GUESS YOU BEAT US
TO THE PUNCH.
BY THE WAY,
SPEAKING OF "PUNCH,"
LIGHTNING PUNCH!
HA HA HA HA!
QUIET.
THERE ARE MORE GUARDS.
I'M NOT A STRING,
I'M A FRAYED KNOT.
HA HA HA HA!
I'M TIRED OF HIDING.
LET'S FIGHT!
YOU HAVE TO LEARN FIGHTING'S
NOT THE ONLY ANSWER.
IT SHOULD ONLY BE
YOUR LAST RESORT.
LET'S GO BACK THIS WAY.
WE'LL COME OUT ON TOP
NEAR THE CONTROL SPIRE.
Patamon: GOOD IDEA!
WHY WON'T ANYONE
LISTEN TO ME?
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
T.K.: HEY, DAVIS,
I ALMOST FORGOT.
I SAW YOUR SISTER TODAY.
YEAH, SO WHAT?
SO NOTHING.
SHE PROBABLY HAD A LOT
OF BAD THINGS TO SAY ABOUT ME.
SHE SAID I BITE MY TOENAILS
AND SPIT THEM ON THE FLOOR,
THAT I USED TO SUCK MY THUMB
UNTIL ABOUT A MONTH AGO,
THAT I WET THE BED
EVERY OTHER THURSDAY...
SHE TALKS TOO MUCH.
WHEN I SEE HER,
I'LL TEACH HER A LESSON.
SHE DIDN'T MENTION
ANY OF THAT.
YOUR SISTER DIDN'T
EVEN MENTION YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH THE BIG MOUTH.
IF YOU'VE GOT A PROBLEM,
WHY DON'T WE SETTLE IT NOW?
COME ON, MATT, DON'T FIGHT.
HE'S YOUNGER THAN YOU ARE.
HE DOESN'T KNOW ANY BETTER.
I DON'T CARE
HOW YOUNG HE IS.
HE BETTER
LEARN SOME RESPECT.
IT'S MY SISTER,
AND IF I WANT
TO CALL HER NAMES,
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
THAT'S ENOUGH, DAVIS!
I CAN'T STAND ANYONE
WHO TALKS BAD
ABOUT THEIR BROTHER
OR SISTER.
ME?
SHE LOVES ME,
SHE HATES ME.
SHE HATES ME-E-E-E!
DAVIS, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IT'S KARI. SHE HATES ME.
SHE THINKS I'M A DISGUSTING,
WORTHLESS PIECE OF DIRT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN DAVIS
SO DEPRESSED.
I'VE GOT TO CHEER HIM UP.
I KNOW!
KNOCK, KNOCK...
HOW DO WE GET DOWN
FROM HERE?
Gatomon: IT'S TOO STEEP!
IF WE HAD A ROPE
WE COULD CLIMB DOWN.
I'LL GO LOOK FOR ONE.
WE'LL BE THE ROPE.
WE'LL JUST HANG
ONTO EACH OTHER,
AND YOU CAN CLIMB DOWN
THE BUNNY SLOPE.
OKAY, LET'S GO!
HA! NO ONE'S GOING ANYWHERE.
DAVIS, IT'S TIME
FOR ACTION!
I'M GOING TO TAKE
THAT OVERGROWN TOMATO
AND TURN HIM
INTO VEGETABLE SOUP.
I'M GOING TO MAKE VEGETARIANS
AROUND THE WORLD PROUD.
THAT OUGHT TO CHEER YOU UP.
V-HEAD BUTT!
AND NOW FOR A SIDE DISH --
CHILI PEPPER PUMMEL!
V-MON! ARMOR DIGEVOLVE!
STINK-GEN!
EWW! P.U.!
[ COUGHING ]
PUT ME DOWN,
OR I'LL TOSS YOU LIKE A SALAD!
IN CASE YOU'VE FORGOTTEN,
I HAVE THE UPPER HAND HERE.
V-MON!
THE KEY TO GOOD COOKING IS
TO ALWAYS TENDERIZE THOROUGHLY
LIKE SO!
IS THAT YOUR BEST SHOT?
WE'RE JUST GETTING STARTED!
HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT FLYING?
I CAN'T WATCH THIS.
V-MON DOESN'T STAND
A CHANCE AGAINST HIM.
V-MON! I'M COMING!
Red Vegimon: COMBINE
ALL YOUR INGREDIENTS
INTO A BOWL.
NEXT, STIR...
BLEND...
MIX...
FRAPPé AND VOILà --
THE FIRST COURSE!
NOW THE ENTRéE!
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP!
I HAVE TO DO MY BEST
TO CHEER DAVIS UP,
WHATEVER THE COST.
[ Thinking ] THIS WHOLE THING
IS MY FAULT.
V-MON IS DOING ALL THIS
JUST FOR ME.
V-MON, YOU CAN STOP NOW!
I'M HAPPY! I'M HAPPY!
YOU ARE? AAH!
HA HA HA HA!
LEAVE HIM ALONE NOW!
HE'S HAD ENOUGH.
I DON'T DOUBT HE'S FEELING
A LITTLE FULL,
BUT HE MUST'VE SAVED ROOM
FOR DESSERT,
AND I'VE COOKED UP
A SWEET SURPRISE!
IF ONLY I COULD DIGEVOLVE.
THERE MUST BE A WAY.
V-MON!
AND NOW HERE'S THE SURPRISE
I PROMISED YOU --
A DOUBLE HELPING OF...
SPIKED PUNCH!
V-MON!
DUCK! NO!
GABUMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
GARURUMON!
WHAT?
Davis: GABUMON,
HOW DID YOU DIGEVOLVE?
GRRAAH!
AAH!
HOWLING BLASTER!
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
V-MON ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
FLAMEDRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
NO!
FLAME FIST!
BOY, AM I GLAD TO SEE YOU,
FLAMEDRAMON.
IT'S TIME
FOR A LITTLE PAYBACK.
I THINK WE SHOULD GIVE
THIS OVERGROWN HOUSEPLANT
A REAL COOKING LESSON.
FLAMEDRAMON, GET HIM!
YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME?
AAH!
THAT HURT.
FIRE ROCKET!
AAH, I'VE HEARD OF GRILLED
VEGETABLES BEFORE,
BUT THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
YOU DID IT!
Yoli: DAVIS!
GARURUMON...
HOW WERE YOU ABLE
TO DIGEVOLVE?
I'M NOT QUITE SURE.
WHEN RED VEGIMON'S PUNCH
CRACKED THE CONTROL SPIRE,
WE WERE FREED
FROM ITS POWER.
THEY'RE CERTAINLY GOING
TO NEED A LOT OF GLUE.
WE SHOULD DESTROY
THE SPIRE,
AND WHO BETTER TO DO THE JOB
THAN DIGMON?
DIGIARMOR, ENERGIZE!
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER!
ROCK CRACKING!
SORRY, I FORGOT
TO YELL "TIMBER!"
WHOA, DID I GET MARRIED
WHILE I WAS ASLEEP?
[ GRUNTING ]
OH, NOW I SEE HOW
IT WORKS.
MAY I INQUIRE AS TO WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
THE SPIRE.
IT ACTED LIKE
AN ELECTRICITY ROD.
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR SET IT UP
TO SEND OUT POWER
TO THE DARK RINGS,
MAKING IT POSSIBLE FOR HIM
TO CONTROL DIGIMON
THROUGHOUT THE AREA.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, IZZY?
YEAH, I'M QUITE IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR THEORY, YOLI.
I WONDER HOW MANY MORE
CONTROL SPIRES THERE ARE
SCATTERED AROUND
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WELL, WHATEVER THE NUMBER IS,
ONE THING WE KNOW FOR SURE
IS THEY ALL
HAVE TO BE DESTROYED.
QUITE A TOUGH MISSION
FOR THE NEW DIGIDESTINED.
WE CAN HANDLE IT.
YOU SAID IT.
SOMEONE SHOULD TAKE
THE GATSUMON BACK
TO THEIR HOMES NOW.
I'M ALL OVER IT.
COME ON!
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
BIG BROTHER.
GARURUMON WILL STAY HERE
AND PROTECT YOU GUYS
FROM THE EMPEROR.
GARURUMON!
I'M GLAD THE GATSUMON AREN'T
STAYING WITH US ANYMORE.
THEY CLAWED THE SINK
WHEN THEY BRUSHED THEIR TEETH.
THEY WERE
KIND OF COOL, THOUGH.
HEY, EVERYONE,
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
WOW, WHAT IS THAT?
I FOUND IT WHEN I WAS EXAMINING
YOUR DIGIVICE, YOLI.
IT SEEMS TO BE A MAP
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
DO YOU SEE THIS WHITE SQUARE?
IT USED TO BE BLACK UNTIL
WE DESTROYED THE CONTROL SPIRE.
THERE ARE A LOT
OF BLACK SQUARES LEFT,
AND THEY ALL HAVE SPIRES.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE TIME TO TURN
BLACK SQUARES INTO WHITE ONES.
AND HOW DO WE KNOW HE WON'T
BUILD NEW SPIRES?
THEY DON'T MAKE
CONTROL SPIRES
LIKE THEY USED TO.
WAY TO GO, GREYMON! YOU'RE
A ONE-MON WRECKING CREW.
WHAT? A SPIRE
WAS DESTROYED?
IT MUST BE
THOSE MEDDLING KIDS.
OH, WELL.
DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
THAT AREA
WAS PRETTY UNIMPORTANT
IN THE GRAND SCHEME.
WITHIN A YEAR,
I WILL HAVE EVERY AREA
UNDER MY FULL CONTROL.
THEN, EVERY LIVING THING
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
WILL BECOME MY SLAVE
FOREVER,
AND THAT INCLUDES
THOSE KIDS, TOO.
HA HA HA HA!
Man: WHAT IS THE DIGIMON
EMPEROR'S MASTER PLAN?
MORE PIECES
TO THE PUZZLE REVEALED
ON THE NEXT "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."