GOMAMON TRIED TO SAVE
THE GIZAMON,
BUT THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
TURNED THEM AGAINST HIM.
JOE AND THE REST OF US CAME
TO THE DIGIWORLD TO HELP OUT
AND TO DESTROY THE NEWEST
OF THE CONTROL SPIRES.
WE SLEDDED RIGHT PAST
THOSE SLOWPOKE SNOWMEN.
HOWEVER, WE ALMOST LOST CODY
TO THE ICY RIVER,
BUT GOMAMON FISHED HIM OUT.
JOE NURSED CODY BACK TO HEALTH,
BUT HIS CURE DIDN'T INCLUDE
BEING ATTACKED BY EBIDRAMON.
THE ARMORED DIGIMON
DESTROYED THE CONTROL SPIRE,
AND IKKAKUMON SAVED THE DAY.
I HOPE THE NEXT CONTROL SPIRE
IS SOMEWHERE A LITTLE WARMER.
♪ DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Woman:
ATTENTION PASSENGERS,
EAST MEETS WEST AIRLINES
WELCOMES YOU TO TOKYO.
AGAIN,
WE APOLOGIZE FOR THE PILOT
STEPPING OUT FOR POPCORN
DURING THE IN-FLIGHT MOVIE.
Man:
WILL THE OWNER OF THE GRAY 747
PARKED OUTSIDE THE WINDOW
PLEASE REPORT TO THE COCKPIT?
YOUR LIGHTS ARE ON.
Woman:
HI. I MISSED YOU.
IT'S SO BRIGHT OUT,
AND I'M WIDE AWAKE.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
8:54 IN THE MORNING!
I'M STILL ON NEW YORK TIME.
I BETTER CHANGE MY WATCH.
THERE.
NOW I'M CAUGHT UP.
[ Yawns ]
OH, I'M EXHAUSTED.
DAVIS, WAKE UP.
[ SNORING ]
DAVIS! DAVIS!
DAVIS, DAVIS!
[ GROANING ]
HUH?
GOOD MORNING.
SLEEP WELL?
YEAH, UNTIL I HEARD
ALL THAT SCREAMING.
THE NEXT TIME I TELL YOU
TO WAKE ME UP,
TRY TO BE A LITTLE QUIETER
SO I CAN GET SOME SLEEP.
I TURN MY BACK ON HIM
FOR ONE MINUTE
AND HE DISAPPEARS.
OPUMON, WHERE ARE YOU?
HMM? OPUMON?
HUH? CODY!
HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU
NOT TO WANDER AROUND
THE HOUSE?
MOM MIGHT THINK
YOU'RE A RODENT.
GUESS WHAT.
I THINK YOUR MOM
IS MAKING US SOME CANDY.
CANDY?
IT'S NOT CANDY.
IT'S SUSHI.
DOES IT TASTE
LIKE CANDY?
NOT REALLY.
IT'S SEAWEED AND RAW FISH.
YUCKY!
I'VE MADE A BED FOR YOU,
GATOMON.
YOU THINK I'M GETTING
IN THERE? THINK AGAIN.
OH, COME ON.
BE A SPORT.
IT'LL BE FUN.
[ MUMBLES ]
I'M LEAVING NOW.
I'LL BE BACK LATER.
OOPS, ONE MORE THING.
PATAMON?
CAN WE HURRY UP?
YOUR GYM SOCKS
FROM YESTERDAY ARE IN HERE.
SORRY. I FORGOT.
OKAY, MOM, I'M PACKED.
BESIDES THE USUAL
I'M ALSO TAKING POTATO SALAD,
MACARONI SALAD, TUNA SALAD,
CHICKEN SALAD, FRUIT SALAD,
AND 3-BEAN SALAD.
ACTUALLY, IT'S ONLY
2-BEAN SALAD TODAY.
I WAS OUT
OF THE THIRD BEAN.
THAT'S AN AWFUL LOT OF FOOD
FOR ONE GIRL.
I TOLD YOU I'M HAVING A PICNIC
WITH THE COMPUTER CLUB TODAY,
SO I OFFERED TO BRING SALAD
FOR EVERYONE.
AND WHO'S PAYING FOR IT?
YEAH, I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
YOLI, WAIT!
YOLI, HURRY. OPEN UP!
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY!
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
PORUMON?
SITTING ON THIS COLESLAW
IS GETTING A LITTLE MESSY,
AND WHAT'S IN HERE
THAT HAS SUCH A FOUL SMELL?
DEVILED EGGS.
P.U.!
PORUMON'S RIGHT.
I CAN SMELL THEM
FROM OVER HERE.
AREN'T THE OTHERS
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE?
YEAH. THEY'RE LATE.
HERE THEY COME NOW.
HEY,
WHAT TOOK YOU GUYS SO LONG?
I STOPPED
AT A DRINKING FOUNTAIN
TO GIVE PORUMON A BATH.
IT'S A LONG STORY.
NEVER MIND. LET'S GO.
ALL CLEAR.
NOW EVERYBODY REMEMBER MY PLAN.
CROUCH!
KEEP CROUCHING.
LISTEN,
I KNOW IT'S A SATURDAY,
AND WE'RE NOT REALLY
SUPPOSED TO BE AT SCHOOL,
BUT NOBODY IS WITHIN MILES
OF THIS PLACE.
I REFUSE TO CROUCH.
ACTUALLY, DAVIS,
I DON'T THINK IT'S REALLY
NECESSARY FOR ME TO CROUCH.
I GOT US HERE.
AM I THE BEST OR WHAT?
[ BOTH SIGH ]
LET'S GO. HEY, I WONDER
IF THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS OPEN ON SATURDAYS.
ALL RIGHT! I GOT US IN.
AM I THE BEST OR WHAT?
All: HUH?
I'M SORRY, BUT ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE?
All: WHOA! MIMI! MIMI?
UM, T.K., KARI?
T.K. and Kari: YEP.
DAVIS, YOLI, CODY,
I WANT YOU TO MEET SOMEONE.
THIS IS OUR FRIEND MIMI.
SHE'S ONE OF THE ORIGINAL
DIGIDESTINED
TO MOVE TO AMERICA.
I'M MIMI.
I'VE SET MY SIGHTS
ON SUCCESS IN THE FASHION WORLD
OF NEW YORK CITY.
DON'T THINK I'M JUST
A STRAWBERRY-BLOND BEAUTY
WHO KNOWS SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
SORA TOLD US
ALL ABOUT YOU.
I SPOKE TO HER.
SHE TOLD ME ABOUT YOU, TOO.
HELLO, MY NAME IS DAVIS,
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME DAVIS.
YEAH, SHE DEFINITELY
TOLD ME ABOUT YOU.
GATOMON, PATAMON,
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
OTHER THAN BEING STUFFED
IN A KNAPSACK
LIKE A WET TOWEL, FINE.
WHEN DID YOU GET BACK?
THIS MORNING.
I WAS PASSING BY THE SCHOOL
AND JUST HAD TO TAKE A LOOK.
I JUST WALKED IN THE FRONT GATE.
SOMEONE LEFT IT OPEN.
THAT WAS US.
WE HAD TO SNEAK IN
SINCE THE SCHOOL WAS CLOSED.
WE DECIDED TO GO ON A PICNIC
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
DIGITAL WORLD?
MAYBE MIMI CAN COME WITH US.
I HAVEN'T BEEN THERE
IN SO LONG.
DO YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE OKAY?
OF COURSE.
WE DIDN'T BRING ENOUGH SODAS
FOR AN EXTRA PERSON.
OH, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
SHE CAN HAVE MY SODA.
MINE, TOO.
PERFECTO! NOW LET'S GO.
NOW THE REST OF US
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO DRINK.
DIGIPORT, OPEN!
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH ♪
HEY, GOOD NEWS, GUYS.
TAKE A LOOK AROUND.
I DON'T SEE
A CONTROL SPIRE ANYWHERE.
DO YOU?
NOT A ONE.
NO, SIRREE.
HOW COOL! I'M BACK.
THE DIGITAL WORLD
HASN'T CHANGED.
[ Thinking ] I WONDER
IF I'LL SEE PALMON AGAIN.
HI.
DIGIMON EMPEROR?
YEAH.
HE BUILDS
THESE CONTROL SPIRES,
TRIES TO TAKE OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
YADA, YADA, YADA.
[ LAUGHS ]
SO IF THERE'S
NO CONTROL SPIRES,
ARE WE SAFE?
YEAH. THAT'S WHY
WE PICKED THIS SPOT.
WE NEVER WOULD'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT HAVING A PICNIC HERE
IN THE OLD DAYS
BECAUSE WE'D BE WORRIED
ABOUT GIANT-SIZED DIGITAL ANTS.
SO FAR EVERY TIME
WE'VE COME HERE
IT'S BEEN TO DESTROY
A CONTROL SPIRE,
BUT SINCE IT'S SATURDAY WE
THOUGHT WE'D HAVE SOME FUN.
WE SHOULD PICK OUT A SPOT
TO LAY OUT THE BLANKET
AND DISH OUT FOOD.
SOUNDS GREAT.
NO, IT DOESN'T.
IT'S WAY TOO EARLY FOR LUNCH.
LET'S KEEP WALKING.
I AM A LITTLE HUNGRY.
HUH? OH.
I'M STARVED. LET'S EAT.
WHY DIDN'T I
THINK OF THAT?
I BROUGHT THESE FROM MY FAMILY'S
CONVENIENCE STORE.
YOU WANT SOME?
IS THAT
WHAT I THINK IT IS --
A CHOCOLATE COVERED
RICE BALL?
I HAVEN'T HAD ONE
SINCE I WAS A KID.
I LOVE THEM.
OH!
[ ALL LAUGH ]
MMM.
WHAT WILL YOU HAVE?
I'LL HAVE WHATEVER
ARMADILLOMON IS HAVING.
HE'S EATING SUSHI.
EXCELLENT.
I'LL HAVE ONE SUSHI,
PLEASE.
COMING RIGHT UP.
NO! NEVER THROW FOOD!
OH, COME BACK,
LITTLE SUSHI!
WAIT, HAWKMON, COME BACK!
IT'S JUST A CALIFORNIA ROLL.
YES, WELL, IT'S ROLLING ALL
THE WAY BACK TO CALIFORNIA.
[ Thinking ] I HAVE
A BAD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
I DON'T LIKE
THAT THEY'RE GOING OFF
INTO THE WOODS ALL ALONE.
HEY, YOLI! HAWKMON!
COME BACK!
WAKE UP.
MIMI, WAKE UP.
I HOPE SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
THE LAST THING
THAT I REMEMBER...
I FELL.
WE ALL DID.
LOOK AT THAT.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S A CONTROL SPIRE.
THAT MEANS
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
CONTROLS THIS AREA.
[ MUMBLING ]
All: HUH?
SOMETHING TELLS ME
THOSE AREN'T TAILLIGHTS
IN A PARKING LOT.
All: OH!
PRINCESS MIMI, PRINCESS MIMI,
PRINCESS MIMI...
Mimi: RELAX.
THEY'RE JUST GECKOMON
AND OTAMOMON.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT,
MIMI?
'CAUSE THEY'RE MY FRIENDS.
THEY DON'T LOOK
TOO FRIENDLY.
NOT WHILE THEY'RE WEARING
THOSE DARK RINGS.
HUH?
All: GET HER!
[ ALL YELLING ]
OH!
GET HER!
AAH!
OH, GOSH, MIMI,
IF THOSE ARE YOUR FRIENDS,
I'D HATE
TO SEE YOUR ENEMIES.
IT'S NOT THEIR FAULT.
[ Thinking ]
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I WISH PALMON WAS HERE
TO PROTECT ME.
POISON IVY!
OH!
OH, PALMON?
[ ALL YELLING ]
WE MUST DESTROY HER!
I THOUGHT
YOU NEEDED A VINE.
[ Crying ] OH, PALMON.
[ Crying ] MIMI.
OH!
OH,
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
I'M HAPPY, TOO.
OH, I'VE NEVER BEEN THIS HAPPY
IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
I'VE NEVER KNOWN WHAT
HAPPINESS WAS UNTIL TODAY.
[ BOTH CRYING ]
Hawkmon:
PLEASE STOP IT.
IF YOU GET ANY HAPPIER,
I'LL START TO CRY.
[ GASPS ]
I'M CAUGHT
IN YOUR VINES.
IN YOUR HAIR.
ON 3 -- 1...2...3.
ENOUGH REMINISCING, MIMI,
WE'VE GOT TROUBLE.
THIS AREA IS CALLED
THE NIGHT FOREST,
AND THE DIGIMON EMPEROR'S
TAKEN CONTROL
OF ALL THE GECKOMON
AND THE OTAMOMON.
I KNOW. WE HAVE TO DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE.
NO PROBLEM.
I'VE BEEN LIVING IN NEW YORK.
COMPARED
TO GETTING A TAXI,
THAT SHOULD BE
A PIECE OF CAKE.
WE CAN'T DESTROY
THE TOWER ALONE.
YOU'D BETTER
CONTACT THE OTHERS
AND LET THEM KNOW
WHERE WE ARE.
RIGHT.
HAWKMON, YOLI,
WHERE ARE YOU?
All: HAWKMON, YOLI,
HUH?
THIS PLACE HAS SOME ECHO.
OH, BOY.
I'M TRYING
TO GET THROUGH TO DAVIS,
BUT SO FAR NO LUCK.
I THINK IT'S FROM YOLI,
BUT THE SIGNAL
IS KIND OF WEAK.
SHE MUST BE NEARBY,
BUT IN WHAT DIRECTION?
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
MUST BE BLOCKING THE SIGNAL.
OH.
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT A WONDERFUL WAY
TO SPEND A RELAXING WEEKEND --
GETTING RID OF UNWANTED WEEDS
IN MY GARDEN.
WORMON...
YES, MASTER.
WHO'S THE DIGIMON DU JOUR?
THE ROACHMON BROTHERS.
EXCELLENT.
SUMMON THEM IMMEDIATELY.
THEY'RE STAYING
AT THE ROACHMON MOTEL.
HA HA HA HA!
THERE'S NO ANSWER.
OH.
Both: NO ANSWER?
WE DIDN'T EVEN HEAR
THE QUESTION.
WE HOPE
WE'RE NOT BUGGING YOU.
HA HA HA HA!
AAH! ROACHES!
Together:
IT'S THE ROACHMON BROTHERS!
HI, I'M ROACHMON.
AND I'M HIS
TWIN BROTHER ROACHMON.
I USE MY GARBAGE DUMP ATTACK
TO TRASH MY ENEMIES.
I THROW YARD SALE BOMBS
TO WIPE OUT OPPONENTS
AND CLEAN OUT MY GARAGE.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THERE WAS A BUNCH OF KIDS.
SO SUE ME.
I HEARD WRONG.
IS IT REALLY THAT HARD
TO WRITE DOWN A MESSAGE?
EXCUSE ME,
BUT DO YOU ALWAYS ARGUE?
Both: THE ROACHMON BROTHERS
DON'T ARGUE.
NOW STAY OUT OF THIS.
Yoli:
SORRY. GO AHEAD.
I THINK I SHOULD USE
MY GARBAGE DUMP ATTACK
TO FINISH THEM OFF.
I'LL JUST USE
MY YARD SALE BOMBS ON THEM.
BETTER YET,
HOW ABOUT NEITHER?
Both: THE ROACHMON BROTHERS
ARE NOT GOING TO TELL YOU AGAIN.
STAY OUT OF THIS.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA, ROACHMON.
LET'S USE BOTH ATTACKS.
ROACHMON, THAT'S THE FIRST
SMART THING YOU'VE SAID.
Both: GARBAGE DUMP!
AAH!
[ COUGHS ]
OH!
THAT'S IT!
THIS IS A DESIGNER BLOUSE!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
NOW WHAT?
SORRY,
BUT I DON'T PLAY.
OH!
RUN!
Both: YARD SALE BOMBS!
[ BOTH YELLING ]
PALMON, DIGEVOLVE!
I CAN'T UNTIL THE CONTROL SPIRE
IS DESTROYED.
THEY WERE 10 FEET AWAY,
AND YOU MISSED THEM.
I MISSED? YOU MISSED.
BOY, FOR BROTHERS,
THEY SURE DON'T GET ALONG
VERY WELL.
[ Thinking ] I'D BE
BEST FRIENDS WITH MY SISTER
IF SHE WAS
SOMEONE LIKE MIMI.
OH, MIMI,
YOU'RE MY BEAUTIFUL SISTER.
YOLI,
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL, TOO,
AND WE LIVE
IN A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE
WITH A BEAUTIFUL GARDEN.
LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL.
YOLI, I DON'T MEAN
TO INTERRUPT YOUR DAYDREAM,
BUT THIS IS A RATHER
PRECARIOUS SITUATION.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S TIME?
RIGHT.
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HAWKMON ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
HOLSMON --
THE WINGS OF LOVE.
YOLI, CLIMB ON MY BACK.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
WOW. THAT ARMOR DIGEVOLVING
IS SO FASHIONABLE.
♪ I'M GOING DIGITAL... ♪
TEMPEST WING!
AAH!
♪ NOW I'M INVINCIBLE... ♪
I FEEL LIKE SOMEONE
SET OFF A BUG BOMB.
NEVER MIND.
THERE'S TWO OF US,
AND ONLY ONE OF HIM.
Both:
ROACHMON FLY SWATTER!
UGH!
HERE THEY COME AGAIN.
ROACHMON EXTERMINATE!
UGH!
♪ THE WHOLE THING
IS TECHNOLOGICAL... ♪
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S IT.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WHAT?
THOSE ROACHMON
DON'T SEEM TO BE TOO SMART.
YOU CAN USE THEM
TO DESTROY THE TOWER.
ALL RIGHT! PERFECTO!
♪ WORLD, WORLD, WORLD... ♪
COME ON, PALMON,
LET'S GET READY.
[ BOTH GROAN ]
HERE THEY COME.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
ROACHMON EXTERMINATE!
♪ LET'S ALL GET DIGITAL ♪
SINCE THESE GUYS
AREN'T TOO BRIGHT...
AAH!
NOW?
NOW.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
PALMON DIGEVOLVE TO...
TOGEMON!
Both: UGH!
NEEDLE SPRAY!
AAH!
TEMPEST WING!
Emperor:
MY SPIRE! AAH!
AAH!
OH!
THEY'VE DESTROYED ANOTHER ONE
OF MY CONTROL SPIRES!
TALK ABOUT A WASTED WEEKEND.
I'M GOING HOME.
LOCK UP WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
ABOUT TIME.
NOW I CAN WATCH
MY SATURDAY CARTOONS.
HEY, LOOK.
IT'S YOLI'S SIGNAL.
IT'S COMING IN
CRYSTAL CLEAR.
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
IT MUST MEAN
THAT THEY'RE ALL OKAY
AND THEY WERE ABLE TO DESTROY
THE CONTROL SPIRE IN THAT AREA.
ALL RIGHT!
WAY TO GO, YOLI!
UGH.
NOW THEY'LL BE FRIENDLY.
YEAH.
LAST THING I REMEMBER
WE WERE AT THE MOTEL.
WE WERE OUT BY THE POOL,
AND YOU TOOK MY TOWEL.
YOU ATE THE LITTLE CHOCOLATE
THEY PUT ON THE PILLOW.
I PUT THOSE CHOCOLATES
ON THE PILLOW.
I BROUGHT THEM FROM HOME.
FROM HOME? THOSE WERE MY
CHOCOLATES IN THE FREEZER.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, IT'S MY FREEZER.
IT'S MY HOUSE!
I'M PAYING RENT!
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU --
THERE ARE SOME FAMILIES
WHERE THEY'RE BETTER OFF
HAVING ONLY ONE CHILD.
IN SOME CASES, THEY
SHOULDN'T HAVE KIDS AT ALL.
IT'S TIME WE LEFT
THESE TWO ALONE.
STAY ON YOUR HALF
OF THE HOUSE!
YOU STAY ON YOURS!
FINE.
HERE COMES DAVIS
AND THE OTHERS.
YOLI, HAWKMON,
WE'RE OVER HERE.
[ CHEERING ]
THEY TOLD US YOU WERE BACK,
BUT WE DIDN'T BELIEVE THEM.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THE DAY
THAT YOU WOULD RETURN TO US.
MIMI...
HUH? TOGEMON?
I WILL
PROTECT THIS AREA NOW.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
I'VE ALWAYS
COUNTED ON YOU.
WHO'S THAT?
THAT'S MIMI'S DIGIMON --
TOGEMON.
WOW.
TOGEMON,
CALL US IF YOU NEED US.
All: GOODBYE, TOGEMON.
DON'T MAKE ME CRY.
RUBBING MY EYES
HURTS TOO MUCH.
AND STAY ON YOUR HALF
OF THE SKY, TOO.
FINE.
BYE, MIMI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
GOODBYE, EVERYONE.
THANKS FOR A GREAT PICNIC.
BYE.
OH, MIMI,
I ALMOST FORGOT.
HUH?
I WANTED TO SAY --
WHEN I GET OLDER,
I WANT TO BE...
JUST LIKE YOU!
OH.
[ LAUGHS ]
PERFECTO!
Man:
WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
BE ABLE TO STOP
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
FROM EXPANDING HIS EMPIRE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."