WHILE THE OTHERS FOLLOWED
THOSE DARK SPORE KIDS AROUND
TO SEE IF THEY WOULD
LEAD THEM TO OWIKAWA,
TAI AND KARI
CAME TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
GABUMON AND I
HAD FOUND OUT
THAT BLACK WARGREYMON
WAS ON EARTH,
AND WE WERE SURE HE WAS
UP TO NO GOOD.
AZULONGMON GAVE ME
ENOUGH ENERGY
TO WARP-DIGIVOLVE,
AND I WENT WITH TAI
TO STOP BLACK WARGREYMON
FROM DESTROYING OWIKAWA.
IMPERIALDRAMON AND I FINALLY
DEFEATED BLACK WARGREYMON.
TURNS OUT HE REALLY WANTED US
TO PUT HIM OUT OF HIS MISERY,
BUT WORMMON GAVE HIM
A PIECE OF HIS MIND.
I THINK HE ACTUALLY
LISTENED TO US THIS TIME.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGIVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
THE GATE
AT HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE
IS SECURE FOR NOW,
BUT WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO SIT HERE FOREVER.
I'M GETTING FROSTBITE.
DO YOU THINK THEY MAKE
MITTENS FOR WINGS?
WE NEED A MORE
PERMANENT SOLUTION,
OTHERWISE DIGIMON
LIKE DAEMON
WILL KEEP TRYING TO BREAK
THROUGH TO THE REAL WORLD.
Man: DESPITE REPORTS
THAT MONSTERS HAVE BEEN
APPEARING WORLDWIDE,
GOVERNMENT AGENCIES
HAVE BEEN HESITANT
TO RESPOND. THEY'VE
DISMISSED THESE SIGHTINGS
AS THE WORK
OF PRACTICAL JOKERS
AND GOOFBALLS.
HOWEVER, RECENT INCIDENTS
HAVE PROMPTED OFFICIALS
TO TAKE THE ISSUE
SERIOUSLY.
IN A PRESS CONFERENCE
TODAY,
IT WAS REVEALED THAT
THESE SO-CALLED MONSTERS
WOULD BE CONSIDERED
UNIDENTIFIED LIFE FORMS.
THE HOME DEFENSE FORCE
IS EXPECTED TO HEAD UP
THE INVESTIGATION.
IN THE MEANTIME,
THE PUBLIC IS BEING
STRONGLY CAUTIONED
NOT TO PANIC,
AND TO STAY CALM,
SO DON'T MONSTER-PROOF
YOUR HOMES YET, FOLKS.
THEY SAY THAT IT'S PROBABLY
NOTHING BUT A SILLY HOAX.
[ MYSTERIOUS CREAKING ]
CODY, DID YOU
HEAR A NOISE?
IT'S JUST
MY STOMACH GROWLING.
I THINK I HEAR IT COMING
FROM SOMEWHERE DOWN THERE.
HEY, IT TOOK
MY PRUNE JUICE!
UH-OH,
I MADE A BOO-BOO.
AND IT CAN TALK!
WHEN FOOD'S PUT
IN FRONT OF ME,
I JUST CAN'T
HELP MYSELF.
SORRY.
WE ALL MAKE MISTAKES.
GRANDPA, I'M SORRY
FOR KEEPING THIS FROM YOU,
BUT IT'S JUST THAT I--
AHA! I KNEW THERE WAS
SOMETHING FISHY GOING ON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
THAT STUFFED ANIMAL'S GOT
MORE THAN COTTON BALLS
IN HIS STOMACH.
YOU CAN'T FOOL ME.
LET ME GUESS,
HE'S NOT FROM THIS WORLD.
HE'S BEEN TRANSPORTED
FROM ANOTHER DIMENSION,
MAYBE A DIGITAL ONE.
AM I HEARING YOU RIGHT,
GRANDPA?
YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE DIGITAL WORLD?
HOW'D YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT IT?
SO THAT'S WHAT YOU KIDS
ARE CALLING IT
THESE DAYS.
WELL, I SUPPOSE IT WAS
ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
I KNEW I'D HAVE
TO TELL YOU AT SOME POINT,
BUT I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO DO IT SO SOON.
YOU SEE, CODY,
IT HAS TO DO WITH YOUR DAD.
WHEN HE WAS JUST
A YOUNG RASCAL LIKE YOU,
HE ALWAYS TALKED
ABOUT GOING
TO SOME STRANGE PLACE
LIKE A DIGITAL WORLD.
YOU MEAN MY DAD
KNEW ABOUT IT, TOO?
I DIDN'T THINK
TOO MUCH OF IT AT FIRST
BECAUSE HE WAS
ALWAYS INTERESTED
IN VIDEO GAMES
AND THINGS OF THAT SORT,
BUT SUDDENLY
HE STARTED DOING THINGS
THAT REALLY
WORRIED ME.
SOMETIMES HE'D BE
PLAYING A GAME,
AND HE'D ACT LIKE HE WAS
SEEING THINGS
THAT NO ONE ELSE DID,
AS IF THE CHARACTERS
ACTUALLY CAME TO LIFE.
HE'D SIT AT THAT TV
FOR HOURS IN A TRANCE.
SOMETIMES HE'D EVEN
CARRY ON CONVERSATIONS,
I THOUGHT
WITH HIMSELF.
IT GAVE ME THE WILLIES,
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
DAD DID THAT?
I THOUGHT HE WAS
PLAYING AROUND,
BUT HE KNEW
THEY WERE REAL.
CODY!
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT PLANNING
ON GOING OUT AGAIN
BY YOURSELF.
OH, COME ON, MOM.
PLEASE.
NO. YOU'VE BEEN OUT
EVERY DAY THIS WEEK,
AND WITH ALL THIS TALK
ABOUT MONSTERS,
IT WORRIES ME.
I'D RATHER YOU STAYED HOME
TODAY, HONEY.
NOTHING'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
BESIDES, MY FRIENDS
ARE EXPECTING ME.
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
ALL THAT MONSTER TALK
IS PROBABLY
JUST RUMORS AND HEARSAY.
HE'LL BE IN GOOD HANDS.
HE AND I ARE GOING TO GO
PRACTICE OUR KENDO.
HUH?
I'LL KEEP
AN EYE ON HIM. RIGHT?
THOSE DESPICABLE DIGIDESTINED
HAVE BEEN SNOOPING AROUND,
KEEPING TABS
ON ALL THE OTHER LITTLE URCHINS.
FORTUNATELY FOR US,
THE DARK SPORES
HAVE BEGUN TO TAKE ROOT
IN THEIR TEENSY,
LITTLE BRAINS,
BUT THERE'S
A SLIGHT COMPLICATION.
THERE'S ONE BRAT WHOSE SPORE
IS ABOUT TO SPROUT EARLY.
THAT COULD BE TROUBLE.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
HMM.
[ Thinking ]
WITHOUT THE DARK SPORE,
I'D JUST BECOME
AN ORDINARY BUMPKIN,
SMALL POTATOES,
DOOMED TO A LIFE OF MEDIOCRITY.
NOW I'LL BE ABLE
TO RISE ABOVE THE CROWD.
THERE YOU ARE, HONEY.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
CAN I SEE?
I'M BUSY!
MM.
[ Thinking ] HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO ACHIEVE PERFECTION
IF INFERIOR PEOPLE
KEEP TRYING TO BUTT IN?
IT'S VERY FRUSTRATING.
SORRY TO BE LATE. MY MOM
DIDN'T WANT ME TO LEAVE.
I DON'T BLAME HER,
BUT I'M SURE GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I'M READY FOR A BREAK.
YOU'D BETTER GO
GET SOMETHING TO EAT
BEFORE IT'S TIME
FOR THE NEXT SHIFT.
A CHOCOLATE BAR
IS CALLING OUT MY NAME.
SEE YA!
YOU MIND BRINGING ME BACK
SOMETHING?
I'D BE DELIGHTED.
HOW ABOUT QUICHE?
I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S QUICHE OR SQUASH,
AS LONG AS IT'S EDIBLE.
[ GIRL SHOUTING ]
UH-OH.
LEAVE MY THINGS ALONE!
NOW GO AWAY!
Woman: I JUST WANTED TO SEE
IF YOU NEEDED ANY HELP.
NO, NO, NO!
THIS IS BAD.
THAT SPORE IS GROWING FAST.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
SHE COULD BREAK GLASS
WITH THAT SCREAM.
IF SHE'S GIVING ME A HEADACHE,
IMAGINE HOW HER MAMA FEELS.
Man: EXCELLENT.
SHE'S PROGRESSING VERY NICELY,
AND THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT,
SO JUST GO HOME.
NO WAY.
I'M NOT MOVING.
DON'T YOU KNOW
THAT PEOPLE WHO DON'T MOVE
NEVER GET AHEAD IN LIFE?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU AFRAID TO IMPROVE YOUR MIND?
COME ON,
WHY BE MERELY ORDINARY?
IT'S BETTER THAN BEING
CONTROLLED BY A FIEND.
NOBODY IS BEING CONTROLLED.
THEY ALL ASKED FOR IT.
ALL I DID
IS GRANT THEIR WISHES.
PERHAPS YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
THAT THEY'LL BECOME
MORE POWERFUL THAN YOU.
IF YOU HAPPEN TO CHANGE
YOUR MIND, LET ME KNOW.
IN THE MEANTIME,
DON'T ATTEMPT TO INTERFERE.
THEY'VE MADE THEIR CHOICE.
IT'S TOO LATE TO TURN BACK.
HOW COULD THEY MAKE A CHOICE?
YOU'RE LYING.
THEY'VE BEEN BRAINWASHED.
YOU MADE THEM ALL
A BUNCH OF FALSE PROMISES.
YOU SAY THEY'RE GOING TO BECOME
SUPERIOR BEINGS,
BUT YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
A SUPERIOR BEING IS SOMEONE WHO
HELPS AND CARES ABOUT OTHERS.
THE NAME ON THAT BAG --
IT SAYS "HITA."
HIROKI.
THAT WAS MY DAD'S NAME.
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
Aquilamon: I BELIEVE
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
Yolei: THERE GOES
OUR LUNCH BREAK.
WE'LL ELIMINATE
THAT LITTLE TWIT.
GUESS I'LL HAVE TO EAT
LATER.
YOU WON'T FEEL LIKE IT
WHEN WE'RE FINISHED WITH YOU.
GET OUT OF HERE.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE
LIKE A COUPLE OF SILLY FOOLS!
I GAVE YOU AN ORDER!
HE COULD HAVE
AT LEAST SAID PLEASE.
REALLY.
GO! DO AS I SAY.
OH! INGRATE.
[ Thinking ] HIROKI'S SON?
HE'S SIMILAR IN SO MANY WAYS,
BUT I CAN'T LET MYSELF
GIVE IN TO WEAKNESS
WHEN I'M SO CLOSE.
OH, HIROKI.
I HAD A VISION FOR THE FUTURE
THAT EVERYONE SAID
WAS IMPOSSIBLE,
BUT YOU ALWAYS ENCOURAGED ME
TO KEEP TRYING.
YEAH!
I NEVER FIT IN AS A KID.
THEY ALL LAUGHED AT ME
AND THOUGHT I WAS STRANGE.
YOU NEVER DID, THOUGH.
IT WAS AS IF WE WERE MADE
FROM THE SAME MOLD.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
WHY SHOULD I CARE?
HE'S GONE.
WHAT A FOOL I WAS.
HAPPINESS IS AN ILLUSION.
LIFE'S UGLY AND CRUEL.
I'VE MOVED ON, SO WHY HAS HE
COME BACK TO HAUNT ME?
HE'S DEAD.
I CAN'T LET HIS MEMORY
KEEP ME FROM MY DESTINY.
YOU WON'T CHANGE MY MIND.
I WON'T LET YOU!
IF THERE WAS ONLY SOME WAY
I COULD SHOW YOU
THE VIRTUAL BEINGS I CREATED,
YOU'D UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO ACCOMPLISH.
I MADE DIGITAL COPIES
OF MY OWN DNA.
THE COPIES
WERE COMPUTER-GENERATED
INTO SOLID IMAGES
OF MY OWN GENETIC ESSENCE.
WELL, YOU'LL NEVER WIN
A BEAUTY CONTEST.
BUT AFTER ALL, IT'S WHAT'S
INSIDE THAT COUNTS,
AND THAT'S NOT MUCH.
Man: WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO TELL ME?
Both: YOU'RE HORRID AND EMPTY,
SO GET OVER IT.
YOU'RE BAITING ME.
NOW, STOP IT!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
AFRAID TO FACE THE TRUTH?
WE REPRESENT THE ESSENCE
OF YOUR UGLINESS.
Both: WE'RE LIVING
YOUR NIGHTMARE!
LIES!
Voice: YOU ARE
JUST A FOREIGN OBJECT.
YOU'RE WRONG!
IT'S MIND-BOGGLING.
WE HAD THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO NIP THOSE KIDS IN THE BUD,
AND HE STOPPED US.
WHAT WAS HE THINKING?
HE'S TWO TACOS SHORT
OF A COMBO PLATTER.
I CAN'T HELP BUT REMEMBER
THAT CONVERSATION
WITH BLACK WARGREYMON.
HE'S A DIGIMON
AND OWIKAWA'S A HUMAN,
SO WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO BE --
CHOPPED LIVER,
VIRTUAL VIRUSES,
HORROR FILM WANNABES?
I'M TELLING YOU, MY DEAR,
THIS IS GIVING ME
A VAST FEELING OF INFERIORITY.
DID I EVER MENTION
YOU'RE THOROUGHLY PATHETIC
WHEN YOU WHINE?
WE'LL GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF IT.
IN THE MEANTIME,
QUIT YOUR HARPING.
YOU'RE EXASPERATING ME.
Cody: I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
Man: BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
I WILL.
GRANDPA?
WHAT IS IT?
I NEED TO KNOW --
WOULD YOU SAY MY DAD
WAS A GOOD GUY?
HMM? YOUR DAD WAS
A VERY GOOD GUY.
HE WAS AS GOOD AS THEY COME.
WHY WOULD YOU ASK ME
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, CODY?
I MET A MAN YESTERDAY
WHO SAID THAT HE'D KNOWN HIM.
I WAS JUST CURIOUS ABOUT IT,
THAT'S ALL.
IS THAT SO?
WHAT WAS THE MAN'S NAME?
HE TOLD ME HIS NAME
WAS OWIKAWA.
REALLY?
WELL, THAT'S VERY INTERESTING.
YOU'RE KEN ICHIJOUJI,
AREN'T YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
DON'T YOU KNOW
THAT SPYING IS RUDE?
I'M SORRY I FOLLOWED YOU.
JUST HEAR ME OUT.
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
SOMETHING I NEED TO KNOW?
AH, PLEASE. WHY SHOULD I CARE
WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY?
NOW THAT YOU'RE
AN ORDINARY KID AGAIN,
YOU'RE JUST AN INSECT TO ME.
YOU GAVE IT ALL UP --
THE BRAINS, THE POWER --
AND FOR WHAT?
SO PEOPLE WOULD LIKE YOU?
NO, SO I WOULD LIKE MYSELF.
POWER GAVE ME NOTHING
BUT LONELINESS.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME,
NORIKO.
THIS ISN'T THE ANSWER.
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE GOING TO
TELL ME THAT THE ANSWER
IS HAVING FRIENDS AND PARENTS
WHO LOVE YOU, RIGHT?
GIVE ME A BREAK.
THAT'S JUST SAD.
I BET YOU DON'T EVEN BELIEVE
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
I'M SURE NOT BUYING IT.
[ Thinking ] THIS IS GOING TO
BE HARDER THAN I THOUGHT,
BUT I HAVE TO KEEP TRYING.
I CAN'T LET HER SUFFER
LIKE I DID.
I'M OUT OF HERE,
SO DO ME A FAVOR.
BUG OFF, INSECT BOY.
YO, KEN. HEY, DUDE!
HEY, WHAT'S WITH HER?
DON'T ASK.
UHH.
AHH!
UH-OH.
BOY, YOU REALLY
MUST HAVE MADE HER MAD.
I'LL SAY.
UHH. AAH!
AAH!
OH, NO! MY HEAD!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Veemon: LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
GLOWING. CAN YOU SEE ANYTHING?
Davis: SHE'S GROWN
A FUNKY HAIRSTYLE.
Wormmon:
THE SPORE IS SPROUTING.
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
SEE IF SHE NEEDS
OUR HELP, GUYS.
WHOA. WEIRD HEAD ORNAMENT.
Veemon: THE FLOWER'S
BLOOMING.
Owikawa: HA HA HA HA.
OWIKAWA.
Davis: AND HIS FAN CLUB.
Ken: WHAT DO THEY WANT?
YOU GET THREE GUESSES,
AND THEY'RE ALL HER.
NO WAY.
RIGHT.
WORMMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
STINGMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
X-VEEMON!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
X-VEEMON...
STINGMON...
DNA DIGIVOLVE TO...
PAILDRAMON!
♪ DIGIMON ---
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
CAN'T ESCAPE!
GAS CORONO-BLASTER!
HEY, PAILDRAMON,
I WANT TO WATCH YOU
KICK THE BUCKET.
FORGET ABOUT THE OTHERS.
WE'VE GOT TO GET THAT GIRL BACK.
ARMADILLOMON
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF KNOWLEDGE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
I'M AFRAID OLD DIGMON'S
FIT TO BE TIED.
THIS OUGHT TO COOL YOU OFF.
HOW WOULD YOU CREEPS
LIKE TO DANCE?
CHILL OUT, PAILDRAMON.
SAVE THE DANCE LESSONS.
YOU MIGHT HURT THE GIRL.
Ken: NORIKO,
GET AWAY FROM HIM.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I WANT TO GET AWAY?
Ken: IT'S NO USE.
SHE'S STILL UNDER HIS CONTROL.
GO BACK TO YOUR PLAYPENS
LIKE GOOD LITTLE BRATS.
Noriko: I'M READY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
Davis: HEY, BIG GUY, CAN YOU
EYEBALL WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Paildramon: UH-OH.
IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S ABSORBING THE FLOWER.
Armadillomon: THAT'S WHAT
I CALL FLOWER POWER.
LET HER GO!
YOU CAN'T STEAL HER ENERGY
JUST TO MAKE YOURSELF
MORE POWERFUL.
YOU'RE JUST USING HER.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
THAT'S YOUR OPINION.
SHE'S DOING THIS
OF HER OWN FREE WILL.
YEAH, MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
THIS IS COOL.
Paildramon:
THE FLOWER'S GONE!
HERE, TAKE HER.
I'VE NO USE FOR HER NOW.
YOU WOULD BE BETTER OFF
IMPROVING YOUR MIND
RATHER THAN WASTING TIME WITH
THIS SAVING-THE-WORLD NONSENSE.
YOU SEE
WHERE IT GOT YOUR FATHER.
HOW DARE YOU TALK
ABOUT MY FATHER LIKE THAT?
HE'D NEVER APPROVE
OF WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
YOU DON'T DESERVE
TO CALL YOURSELF HIS FRIEND.
OH, MY, I BELIEVE YOU'VE GONE
AND UPSET THE LITTLE FELLOW.
[ Thinking ]
HE'S SO MUCH LIKE HIS FATHER,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
I LOOK INTO HIS EYES.
HIROKI WAS ALWAYS
ON THE SIDE OF JUSTICE.
BUT THOSE DAYS ARE GONE.
Paildramon: THIS ISN'T
A GOOD SIGN AT ALL.
THE ENERGY HE RECEIVED
FROM THE FLOWERS
APPEARS TO BE FORMING
A FORCE FIELD BEHIND HIM.
WHAT COULD IT BE?
Paildramon: WE CAN'T
UNDERESTIMATE HIS POWER.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE IN FOR A FIGHT.
WELL, I HOPE IT ISN'T
GOING TO TAKE LONG.
WE DIDN'T GET ANY LUNCH.
AAH!
IT'S BLACK WARGREYMON.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I CAN FEEL IT.
OWIKAWA,
YOU MUST BE STOPPED.
TERROR DESTROYER!
AAH!
AND NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
LOOKS LIKE I'M JUST IN TIME.
THE POWER
OF THE FORCE FIELD
ATTRACTED HIM LIKE A MAGNET.
MAYBE HIS DOMINATION
OVER THE DIGITAL WORLD
IS THREATENED.
I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
HE'S NOT VERY HAPPY ABOUT IT.
BLACK WARGREYMON,
THIS IS DANGEROUS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
THERE'S A DARK INFLUENCE
PERMEATING THAT CLOUD,
AND I NEED TO FIND OUT
WHAT IT IS.
OWIKAWA, WE HAVE
UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
HAVE YOU COME BACK
TO FACE THE TRUTH? PERFECT.
I CAN MAKE USE OF THE ENERGY
FROM THE CONTROL SPIRES
THAT CREATED YOUR IMAGE.
YOU'RE ONLY A HUMAN.
MY POWER FAR SURPASSES YOU.
YOU'D BE SIGNING
YOUR OWN DEATH WARRANT.
STOP FLATTERING YOURSELF.
YOU'RE SIMPLY
AN ELECTRONIC BEING.
DID YOU CREATE
YOUR TWO FLUNKIES
BECAUSE YOU WERE AFRAID
TO BE ALONE?
[ Gasps ] GRR.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
CAT GOT YOUR TONGUE?
THAT'S ABSURD. DO YOU REALLY
THINK I'M THAT FOOLISH?
I CAN OBLITERATE YOU
IN A HEARTBEAT.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
THIS COULD GET UGLY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE WAS
FRIENDS WITH CODY'S DAD.
THAT GUY'S GOT SOME
MAJOR ISSUES TO WORK OUT.
Yolei: CODY!
MY WORD, THIS IS GETTING
EXTREMELY COMPLICATED.
WHAT'S BLACK WARGREYMON
DOING BACK HERE
AND WHAT'S
WITH THE PURPLE CLOUD?
DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU THINK THAT POWER IS
GOING TO BRING YOU HAPPINESS?
IF YOU DO, THEN YOU'RE LIVING
IN A DREAM.
POWER ISN'T GOING TO HELP YOU
ESCAPE THE LONELINESS YOU FEEL
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY FRIENDS.
IT JUST MAKES IT WORSE.
TAKE IT FROM ME.
THE MORE POWERFUL YOU GET,
THE MORE ALONE YOU BECOME.
CAN'T TAKE THE TRUTH,
CAN YOU?
I CAME AS FAST AS I COULD.
GRANDPA.
I'M SORRY TO GET HERE
SO LATE, MY BOY.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
BUT I REMEMBER YOU WERE
A GOOD FRIEND OF HIROKI.
YOU NEVER HAD MANY FRIENDS,
AND I ALWAYS THOUGHT YOU WERE
A BIT OF AN ODD DUCK,
BUT I NEVER IMAGINED
YOU'D GO COMPLETELY MAD.
HUH? WHO ARE YOU?
WANT TO KNOW HOW I KNOW YOU
SO WELL, YUKIO?
YOU SEE,
I'M CODY'S GRANDFATHER
AND HIROKI'S FATHER.
HIS FATHER?
YOU TWO SPENT HOURS TOGETHER
PLAYING GAMES
AND MAKING UP
OUTRAGEOUS STORIES.
YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVED
THE CHARACTERS WERE REAL.
YOU WERE SO LOST
IN THIS WORLD
I THOUGHT
YOUR MINDS WOULD ROT.
PRETTY SOON, I HAD TO
PUT MY FOOT DOWN
AND BRING AN END TO IT.
YOU BOTH TOOK IT VERY HARD.
I STILL REMEMBER
THE SAD LOOKS ON YOUR FACES.
YOU WERE MISERABLE.
THINGS NEVER CHANGED
AS YOU GREW UP.
YOU STILL SPENT
LONG PERIODS OF TIME
DREAMING ABOUT THAT STRANGE
OTHER WORLD OF YOURS.
YOU NEVER LET ANYONE ELSE
SHARE IN YOUR THOUGHTS
BECAUSE IF YOU DID,
YOU WERE AFRAID
THEY WOULD TAKE THEM AWAY.
THEN ONE DAY IT HAPPENED.
HIROKI WAS GONE FOREVER.
YOU WERE BESIDE YOURSELF
WITH GRIEF.
YOU BECAME
A LOST AND LONELY SOUL.
IT WASN'T NORMAL,
BUT THEN, HIROKI HAD BEEN
YOUR ONLY FRIEND.
I WISH I COULD HAVE
SEEN IT COMING.
I WOULD HAVE TRIED
TO MAKE IT EASIER FOR YOU.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
SO SAD IN MY LIFE.
I HAVE TO SAY IT WAS
A VERY DIFFICULT THING TO WATCH.
YOU MAY NOT BE INTERESTED
IN HEARING THIS,
BUT I'D LIKE TO BE
YOUR FRIEND.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO TALK
TO SOMEONE ABOUT MY SON.
DO YOU THINK
THAT WOULD BE ALL RIGHT?
HUH? YOU MUST MISS HIM
EVEN MORE THAN I DO.
UHH!
AHH!
GRR.
GET AWAY FROM THERE,
GRANDPA!
Armadillomon: HE'S NOT LOOKING
TOO NEIGHBORLY TO ME.
Both: BLACK WARGREYMON!
Cody: WOW. DID YOU SEE THAT?
HE PROTECTED GRANDPA.
HA HA HA HA!
OH, NO! YOU!
IT CAN'T BE. NO!
T.K.: THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
MORE TO THIS THAN WE CAN SEE.
HOW COULD I HAVE BEEN
SO BLIND?
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
YOU'RE PERFECTLY RIGHT
ABOUT BEING ALONE.
WE'RE BOTH DOOMED
TO REMAIN THIS WAY FOREVER.
THERE ISN'T ANY OTHER CHOICE.
HE'S CONTROLLING YOU.
THIS CHANGES EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE VERY PERCEPTIVE
FOR SOMEONE SO NARROW-MINDED.
I HAVE TO HARVEST
ALL THE DARK SPORES
IN ORDER FOR ME TO FULFILL
MY DEEPEST DESIRE.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
HA HA HA HA HA!
HE MUST NOT BE ALLOWED
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD
EVER AGAIN!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, AGAIN?
AGAIN? NOBODY EVER
TELLS ME ANYTHING.
YOU ALL RIGHT, BIG GUY?
MY BODY'S NOT GOING TO LAST
MUCH LONGER.
THE IMAGE CREATED
BY THE CONTROL SPIRES
WILL SOON START
TO BREAK UP,
BUT THERE'S STILL SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO.
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
NO. MY STRENGTH IS MY FINAL GIFT
TO YOU, MY FRIENDS.
I WILL SEAL
THE HIGHTON VIEW TERRACE GATE
WITH MY OWN BODY.
DON'T DO IT.
I MUST.
AAH!
HE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
MEANINGFUL WITH HIS LIFE.
I'D SAY
THIS DEFINITELY QUALIFIES.
BLACK WARGREYMON.
BLACK WARGREYMON!
Voice: I WISH THERE HAD BEEN
ANOTHER WAY.
OOH! WHAT'S THAT?
AHH.
THANK YOU,
BLACK WARGREYMON.
YOU'RE A TRUE A FRIEND,
AND I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU.
BLACK WARGREYMON
SEALED THE GATE,
BUT WILL THE IMPOSTOR
THAT'S CONTROLLING OWIKAWA
FIND A WAY TO GET THROUGH?
FIND OUT
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
OF "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."