Yolei: MY HEART WAS
ALL AFLUTTER WHEN I FOUND OUT
DAVIS' SOCCER TEAM
WAS PLAYING
AGAINST DREAMY SUPERSTAR
KEN THE ROCKET.
DAVIS STARTED OUT GREAT,
BUT KEN RAN CIRCLES AROUND HIM.
CODY DISCOVERED ANOTHER
CONTROL SPIRE IN THE DIGIWORLD,
BUT THE GROUND SWALLOWED US UP.
THE EMPEROR MADE DAVIS CHOOSE
WHICH ONE OF US
WOULD BE FED TO THE DELTAMON
WHEN SUDDENLY WE SHOWED UP.
IT WAS JUST
THE EMPEROR'S SICK JOKE.
WE CRUSHED THAT CONTROL SPIRE,
BUT MY HEART WAS CRUSHED, TOO,
BECAUSE WE FOUND OUT
THAT MY DREAMBOAT KEN
IS REALLY THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
[ Thinking ] THE EMPEROR'S
NOT IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY,
WHICH IS LIKE
EVERY OTHER DAY.
MAYBE I CAN CHEER HIM UP.
HEY, KEN, DID YOU HEAR
THE ONE ABOUT -- OOH!
I GUESS YOU HEARD
THAT ONE ALREADY.
MASTER,
WHAT ARE YOU WATCHING?
JOIN US AS WE TALK
WITH YOUNG GENIUS
KEN ICHIJOUJI.
I'M JUST YOUR AVERAGE
BOY GENIUS.
YOU'RE SO MODEST.
DO YOU SPEND A LOT
OF TIME STUDYING?
SOME GENIUSES DO,
BUT I'D RATHER PLAY SOCCER.
AND FUNNY, TOO.
THEY SAY GENIUS IS 1%
BRAINS AND 99% HARD WORK.
DO YOU THINK THAT'S TRUE?
MINE'S 2%.
AND TO THINK YOU CAME
FROM SUCH HUMBLE BEGINNINGS
IN AN EVERYDAY
APARTMENT BUILDING.
ARE YOU GLAD YOU'RE JUST
AN AVERAGE KID?
THERE'S NOTHING I LOVE
MORE THAN BEING AVERAGE.
SO, YOU'VE MASTERED CHESS,
3-D CHESS,
AND THE DONKEY MADNESS
VIDEO GAME.
IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU CAN'T HANDLE?
REPORTERS.
WHAT DOES A GENIUS
DO FOR FUN
WHEN HE'S NOT SOLVING
COMPLEX MATH PROBLEMS?
THOUGH I KNOW THAT MATH
IS ALREADY MORE FUN
THAN MOST PEOPLE
CAN HANDLE.
I'M ALWAYS BUSY
WRITING COMPUTER PROGRAMS,
BUT LIKE I SAID EARLIER,
MY FAVORITE THING TO DO
IS PLAY SOCCER.
I'M SURE YOU'LL BE
A BIG SUCCESS AT THAT, TOO.
I DON'T SEE HOW ANYTHING
COULD POSSIBLY
GET IN YOUR WAY.
[ GRUMBLES ]
WELL, THAT ABOUT
WRAPS IT UP.
THANKS
FOR YOUR TIME, KEN.
BEST OF LUCK.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
THAT WENT WELL,
DON'T YOU THINK, KEN?
OF COURSE. I ALWAYS
LOOK GOOD TO THE PRESS.
THAT 1%, 2% STUFF
WAS BRILLIANT,
ALTHOUGH I DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT MUCH.
I'LL EXPLAIN IT
TO YOU LATER.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
YOU CAN HELP ME WITH, TOO.
HOW DO YOU GET PAST
LEVEL 4 ON DONKEY MADNESS?
I CAN'T GET THE SCEPTER
WITH THE THING.
I WOULDN'T TELL ANYONE ELSE
YOUR GAMING SECRETS.
I'LL BE SHUSHING NOW.
I'D BE GLAD TO TELL YOU
EVERYTHING I KNOW.
I'LL EVEN COME OVER
AND HELP YOU PLAY THE GAME --
THAT IS, IF YOU DON'T
THINK YOU'RE TOO OLD
TO BE PLAYING VIDEO GAMES.
OH, YEAH, TOO OLD.
I ALWAYS FORGET I'M AN ADULT.
LOOK AT THE TIME.
I'VE GOT TO GET
TO MY ADVANCED
JOYSTICK CLASS.
CAN YOU DO
ONE MORE THING FOR ME?
WHAT IS IT?
UM...AUTOGRAPH.
HMM.
HERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE THE BEST --
BETTER EVEN
THAN A GRAPHICS
ACCELERATOR CARD EVEN.
NOW I GOT THE WHOLE THING
WITH THE HEY AND THE HO.
FOOL.
CHEER UP. YOU CAN DESTROY
SOMEBODY TOMORROW.
OH, KEN, HONEY,
YOUR DINNER
IS READY, DEAR.
HMM.
KEN, IT'S GETTING COLD.
IT'S YOUR FAVORITE, DEAR --
LIVER, SQUASH,
AND LUMPY
MASHED POTATOES.
SAW YOU ON THE TV
TODAY, TIGER.
SOON YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A STICK
TO KEEP ALL
OF THE LADIES AWAY,
JUST LIKE YOUR OLD DAD.
I'VE LOST MY APPETITE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NOTHING.
LOOK AT ALL OF THOSE FOOLS
OUT THERE,
DREAMING AWAY
THEIR MEANINGLESS LIVES,
RUNNING AROUND
LIKE RATS IN A MAZE.
NOT ONE OF THEM IS WORTH
HALF OF WHAT I'M WORTH.
[ GROWLS ]
NOTHING BUT FOOLS!
MASTER? MASTER?
MASTER, I'M -- OOH!
DON'T BE DEPRESSED.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
LET'S GRAB SOME DARK RINGS.
WE'LL CAPTURE A COUPLE
OF INNOCENT DIGIMON
AND MAKE THEIR LIVES
ABSOLUTELY MISERABLE.
THAT SHOULD
MAKE YOU HAPPY.
YOU MEAN KEN
IS THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
RIGHT. AND AS EMPEROR,
HE'S NOT JUST A GENIUS,
HE'S AN EVIL GENIUS.
AND A SUPER-EVIL
GENIUS AT THAT.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY SUCH A SMART PERSON
WOULD USE THEIR GIFTS
TO HURT OTHERS.
HE SEEMED SO NICE.
THERE WAS A REPORT
ON HIM ON TV YESTERDAY
ON THAT SHOW
"THE GENIUS PARADE."
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
IS A KID LIKE US.
LET'S FIND HIM.
WHAT? FIND HIM?
YEAH. WE'LL TRACK HIM DOWN
AND CONFRONT HIM
OUTSIDE THE DIGITAL WORLD.
DOES THIS PLAN INCLUDE
A PART WHERE WE EAT?
FOR YOU, ANYTHING.
HEY, I WONDER
WHERE YOLEI COULD BE.
HEY, EVERYBODY,
SORRY I'M LATE,
BUT LOOK WHAT I'VE GOT!
CHOCOLATE!
COOKIES!
FISH!
ICE CREAM! ICE CREAM!
ICE CREAM!
YOU'RE THE BEST, YOLEI.
YOU COULD BE HEAD CHEF
IN THE CAFETERIA ONE DAY.
SO, YOU'RE NOT HUNGRY?
WHAT?
All: MMM. MMM.
I'M SURPRISED THEY DIDN'T
EAT MY ARM RIGHT OFF.
OH, I FOUND THIS.
THERE'S AN ARTICLE IN IT
ABOUT KEN.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
HEY, YOU GAVE ME
A PAPER CUT.
YEAH, THAT'S HIM,
THE EVIL KID.
WHO WOULD THINK THAT
SUCH A NORMAL-LOOKING BOY
COULD BE
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
HIS SMILE MAKES HIM
LOOK SO GENTLE.
YEAH, BUT HIS HAIRCUT
MAKES HIM LOOK
LIKE YOU, KARI.
LET ME SEE IT.
OH, THIS KID.
I'VE SEEN HIM
ON THE NEWS BEFORE.
LOOK AT HIS I.Q.
HE COULD PROGRAM MY COMPUTER
ANY DAY.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
HE MAY BE SMART,
BUT THAT GUY IS COMPLETELY
ROTTEN TO THE CORE!
HE'S NOT JUST SMART,
HE'S GOT DASHING
GOOD LOOKS, TOO.
AND HE'S ALSO
REALLY ATHLETIC.
HEY, I'M JUST AS GOOD
AT SPORTS AS THAT GUY IS!
OKAY, OKAY, DON'T GET
YOUR KNICKERS IN A TWIST.
LET'S JUST FIND HIM.
WHAT ARE KNICKERS?
NEVER MIND.
I'LL USE MY MAP PROGRAM
TO LOCATE THE APARTMENT BUILDING
BEHIND KEN IN THIS PICTURE.
Yolei: LOOKS LIKE
A NICE PLACE TO LIVE.
Davis: IF LIVING NEXT
TO A HEARTLESS KID IS NICE.
IF MY CALCULATIONS ARE CORRECT,
HE SHOULD LIVE
RIGHT AROUND HERE.
YEAH, I KNOW THAT AREA.
YOU SMUDGED MY SCREEN!
THERE'S AN APARTMENT BUILDING
UNDER KARI'S FINGERPRINT.
Woman: KEN!
KEN?
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, USUALLY I HEAR
THE FURIOUS SCRIBBLE
OF HIM DOING MATH PROBLEMS,
BUT TODAY, NOTHING.
HE'S BEEN AWFULLY QUIET
SINCE THAT SOCCER GAME.
I DON'T WANT TO BARGE IN.
I MIGHT SET OFF
ONE OF HIS BOOBY TRAPS.
WHEN YOU MET
WITH HIS TEACHER,
DID HE SAY ANYTHING
AT ALL TO YOU?
NO, ALL HIS TEACHER
COULD TALK ABOUT
WAS SOMETHING CALLED
DONKEY MADNESS.
DONKEY MADNESS?
I KNOW, IT'S STRANGE.
WE DON'T EVEN OWN
A DONKEY.
LET'S GO IN THERE.
SHOULD WE DO THAT?
I SAY WE BREAK DOWN
THE DOOR.
WHAT?
NO, DON'T BREAK IT DOWN.
WELL, I'VE GOT TO
BREAK SOMETHING.
UHH!
OOH.
KEN?
OH!
LOOK AT THIS!
WHAT'S THIS?
"GOODBYE TO ALL OF YOU.
"YOUR TRIVIAL LIVES
WILL PLAGUE ME NO LONGER.
MY DESTINY AWAITS."
NO! HE'S RUN AWAY.
[ CRYING ]
HERE IT IS.
THIS IS WHERE WE STOP KEN
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
OKAY, I WROTE DOWN
A BATTLE PLAN.
UH, DOES IT INCLUDE
THE POLICE?
HUH? MAN,
THAT KID'S TROUBLE.
Woman: LITTLE KEN ICHIJOUJI
IS MISSING,
AND NO ONE HAS ANY IDEA
WHERE HE MIGHT BE.
I THINK
HE'S RUN AWAY FROM HOME.
RUN AWAY FROM HOME?
I BET I KNOW
WHERE HE'S GONE.
SPEAK TO ME, JUST TWO WORDS.
ONE, EVEN.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
KEN IS PROBABLY
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT IT'S DANGEROUS
TO JUST RUSH IN THERE.
BUT THE LONGER WE WAIT,
THE MORE TIME HE HAS
TO PLOT AGAINST US.
WE NEED TO MAKE
A NEW PLAN.
WE NEED TO KNOW
WHAT KEN'S DOING.
LET'S CHECK THE COMPUTER.
DOES THAT MEAN
WHAT I THINK IT MEANS?
KEN IS TAKING OVER AREAS
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
FASTER THAN EVER BEFORE.
WELL, THEN LET'S GO.
WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO BE RECKLESS.
REMEMBER THE EXPRESSION
"FOOLS RUSH IN
WHERE ANGELS FEAR TO TREAD."
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
BEING A FOOL IS REALLY LOW
ON MY PRIORITY LIST,
BUT I CAN'T SIT HERE
AND DO NOTHING.
WHY DO EVIL GENIUSES
HAVE TO BE SO EVIL?
HE DOESN'T LOOK CABAPLE
OF CAUSING SUCH TROUBLE.
WELL, HE IS,
AND DON'T LET
YOURSELF FORGET IT.
HMPH!
WELL, I'VE HAD ENOUGH TALK.
I'M GETTING TICKED OFF.
I WANT SOME ACTION.
HE'S RIGHT, SO LET'S
GET IT INTO GEAR.
I'M WITH YOU.
LET'S FIGHT.
YOU'VE CONVINCED ME.
NO MORE HESITATION.
EXCELLENT!
DIGIPORT, OPEN.
LET'S GO GET
THAT EVIL CUTE GUY!
I'LL BE WATCHING OVER YOU.
GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
IT'S GENIUS-STOPPING TIME!
LET'S GO!
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ OH-OH, OH-OH,
OH-OH-OH ♪
OH-OH-OH-OH ♪
THEY'RE HERE.
HA!
LOOK AT THIS LAND OF FIRE.
IT'S LIKE THE MOVIE
"LAND OF FIRE."
IT SURE IS HOT.
5-STAR-CHILI HOT.
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME FIGHT
INSTEAD OF CAPTURING GREYMON?
YOU FIGHT? HMPH.
[ WHIMPERING ]
I GUESS I'LL TAKE THAT
AS A NO.
MASTER, CAN I GET
A LITTLE HELP HERE?
I'M HAVING
SOME TROUBLE STANDING.
I'M OKAY.
HA HA HA HA!
THAT CONTROL SPIRE
WILL BE THEIR DOOM.
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
TROUBLE COULD BE ANYWHERE.
[ ALL GASP ]
MERAMON!
MERAMON ARE VERY DANGEROUS.
THEY CAN BURN YOU
WITH THEIR ROARING FLAME ATTACK
OR JUST BY TOUCHING YOU.
LET'S SHOW THEM
WHO'S BOSS!
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
VEEMON, ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLAMEDRAMON,
THE FIRE OF COURAGE!
AAH!
ROARING FLAME!
FIRE ROCKET!
UHH! HA HA.
DON'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
YOU'RE JUST TICKLING HIM.
I DON'T THINK FIRE ATTACKS
ARE GOING TO WORK ON THEM.
MY TURN.
GET THEM, HAWKMON!
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HAWKMON, ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
HALSEMON, THE WINGS OF LOVE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
TEMPEST WING!
OHH.
HALSEMON, STOP!
YOU'RE MAKING
THE FLAMES BIGGER!
Emperor: THERE'S MY PREY.
COME AND GET IT!
WHAT DO YOU SAY
THE TWO OF US GO AT IT,
ONE-ON-ONE?
AS MUCH AS I APPRECIATE
YOUR OFFER,
I'D RATHER REPLACE
FEAR THROW.
WHAT?
BUT I HATE FEAR THROW.
NOTHING IS WORKING.
IT'S UP TO YOU, ARMADILLOMON.
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADILLOMON,
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
DIGMON, THE DRILL OF POWER!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ROCK CRACKING!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
WAY TO GO!
LOOK!
WATCH OUT!
NOTHING STOPS THEM!
HERE THEY COME!
MY TURN?
LET'S DO IT!
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
PATAMON, ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
PEGASUSMON, FLYING HOPE!
TEMPEST WING!
IT'S WORKING!
STAR SHOWER!
ARE YOU READY?
ALWAYS AM.
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
GATOMON, ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
NEFERTIMON,
THE ANGEL OF LIGHT!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
Emperor: SENDING GREYMON
TO ATTACK THOSE KIDS
IS MY BEST PLAN YET.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE PROBLEMS
YOU HAD WITH ANDROMON?
I LEARNED FROM MY MISTAKES.
IF I CAN MAKE
A DIGIMON DIGEVOLVE
WHILE UNDER MY CONTROL,
THEN I CAN CONTROL
ITS OTHER FORMS AS WELL.
YOU GIVE ME CHILLS
WHEN YOU ACT ALL TOUGH.
OH, BE QUIET.
GREYMON,
DIGEVOLVE TO METALGREYMON
AND BE MY SLAVE!
[ ROARS ]
GREYMON, DIGEVOLVE TO...
SKULLGREYMON!
ROSETTA STONE!
AAH!
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR PLAYING WITH FIRE.
[ SNARLING ]
OH, NO!
IT'S SKULLGREYMON!
THE ONLY THING MORE TERRIFYING
THAN HIS LOOKS
ARE HIS FIGHTING SKILLS,
ESPECIALLY HIS
DARK SHOT ATTACK.
SKULLGREYMON...
[ ROARS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AAH!
[ ROARS ]
SUDDENLY THIS PLAN DOESN'T
REALLY SEEM SO GOOD.
[ GRUNTS ]
HOW CAN WE BEAT THAT THING?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
[ GRUNTING ]
NOT EVEN ONE?
I HAVE ONE.
WHAT?
I SAY WE RUN
AND THEN RUN SOME MORE.
FIRE ROCKET!
HE GOT FLAMEDRAMON!
DIGMON, NO!
[ ROARS ]
HALSEMON!
[ SNARLING ]
EVERYONE, RUN!
BUT WE HAVE TO
FIGHT SKULLGREYMON.
GREAT IDEA --
STAY CLUSTERED TOGETHER
SO YOU CREATE AN EASY TARGET.
GET TO SAFETY!
DARK SHOT!
HE'S GOT GOOD AIM.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
I SHOULD PROBABLY
HAVE PUT ON MY GOGGLES.
[ SNARLING ]
YOU WANT TO PLAY ROUGH?
I'M AFRAID TO FIND OUT
WHO HE'S CALLING.
WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
[ ROARS ]
THEY'RE DARKTYRANNOMON.
A COMPUTER PROGRAM
TURNED TYRANNOMON
INTO THE EVIL DARKTYRANNOMON.
WATCH OUT FOR HIS
FIRE BREATH ATTACK.
WHY CAN'T WE EVER
FIGHT ANYTHING SHORT,
LIKE SOME MICE?
♪ 'CAUSE EVERYTHING
HAS GONE WAY TOO FAR ♪
THEY CAN BAKE, BOIL,
AND BRAISE HIM.
IF HE CAN'T STAND THE HEAT,
HE'D BETTER GET OUT
OF THE KITCHEN.
STOP. YOU'RE MAKING ME
WANT TO BARBECUE.
♪ IT'S GETTING DIGITAL, MAN ♪
♪ IT STARTS HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN ♪
HE'S THROWING THEM AROUND
LIKE RAG DOLLS. PAINFUL.
HOPE HE DOESN'T GET THE IDEA
TO THROW US AROUND.
♪ IT'S GETTING DIGITAL, MAN ♪
♪ IT STARTS HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN ♪
HE BEAT THEM ALL
SINGLE-HANDED.
IT'S THE STRANGEST THING.
THAT'S AGUMON.
THAT SLIMY CREATURE
IS COMING AFTER HIM.
AND WHEN I SAY SLIMY CREATURE,
I MEAN KEN.
AGUMON!
LET HIM GO.
YOU'D BETTER NOT
HURT HIM, KEN!
YEAH, JERK!
FROM DEFEAT
I SNATCH ANOTHER VICTORY.
HA HA HA!
T.K., DAVIS,
SOMEBODY DO SOMETHING!
THEY'RE GETTING AWAY!
OHH.
WHOA, THAT'S
THE STRANGEST THING I'VE SEEN
SINCE MY ETHERNET CONFIGURATION
COLLAPSED.
[ Gasps ] WHAT?
THE ENTIRE AREA
THAT AGUMON WAS GUARDING
HAS BEEN TAKEN OVER
BY THE DIGIMON EMPEROR.
DOES THAT MEAN THAT AGUMON
IS UNDER HIS CONTROL?
OR WORSE YET,
WHAT IF AGUMON'S BEEN DESTROYED?
THEN WHO'S NEXT?
IF HE WAS ABLE
TO GET AGUMON,
THAT MEANS EVERY ONE
OF OUR DIGIMON ARE IN DANGER.
HOW WILL THE DIGIDESTINED
RESCUE AGUMON?
THE ANSWER ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."