Davis: THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL,
I MET THIS NEW KID T.K.,
WHO I THINK
HAS A THING FOR KARI.
THEN IZZY SHOWS UP,
AND I FIND OUT
TAI'S IN TROUBLE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
YOLEE, CODY, AND I GOT
THESE COOL NEW DIGIVICES,
BUT ONLY KARI AND T.K. AND I
GOT TO GO THROUGH THE GATE.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE
ALL THOSE DIGIMON.
WE FOUND
THE DIGI-EGG OF COURAGE,
BUT ONLY I WAS ABLE TO LIFT IT,
NATURALLY.
THAT'S WHEN I MET V-MON,
WHICH IS GOOD.
HE TAUGHT ME
HOW TO OPEN THE DIGI-EGG.
FLADRAMON IS RAD,
BUT THAT EVIL DIGIMON EMPEROR
LOOKS LIKE A LOT OF TROUBLE.
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE THE DIGITAL ♪
♪ WORLD ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGEVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ♪
WHERE ARE WE?
THIS IS THE COMPUTER ROOM.
HEY, WHEN YOU GUYS
CAME THROUGH THE COMPUTER,
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
THAT PLACE IS THE COOLEST EVER.
THERE WE WERE,
WHEN SUDDENLY A DINOSAUR-LIKE
DIGIMON ATTACKED.
THAT'S WHEN
I JUMPED NTO ACTION.
ENOUGH! LET'S GO BACK.
I THINK WE'VE HAD ENOUGH
EXCITEMENT FOR ONE DAY.
DON'T YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD, CODY?
SEEING ALL THOSE MONSTERS
AND STUFF WOULD BE FUN,
BUT TONIGHT'S MACARONI
AND CHEESE NIGHT AT MY HOUSE
AND I DON'T WANT
TO MISS OUT.
IT'S PORK SURPRISE
AT MY PLACE.
STUFFED
GREEN PEPPERS.
TV DINNERS
IN THE MICROWAVE.
NO FAIR.
I WANT TO GO!
DON'T WORRY, YOLEE,
YOU'LL GET A CHANCE.
WHEN?
OOPS, I ALMOST FORGOT
TO TURN OFF THE COMPUTER.
THE GATE'S CLOSED.
Boy: LEAVING ALREADY, MATT?
WE'RE NOT DONE WITH REHEARSAL.
O . THEAÃSOME
TAKE
I'VE GO
HERE HE COMES.
I'M L
SR HY, VER
I WONDER WHAT
IT'S REALLY LIKE
TO ACTUALLY TRAVEL
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
I DON'T CARE
IF THEY DON'T WANT ME.
TOMORROW I'M GOING
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
Woman: YOLEE, ARE YOU
STAYING FOR DINNER?
NO, BUT THANKS ANYWAY.
I HAVE TO GET GOING.
BOY, I JUST CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT V-MON.
DIGI-ARMOR ENERGIZE, HUH?
IT WAS A FORM OF DIGEVOLVING
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
SOMEHOW, DAVIS' DIGIMON
WAS ABLE TO DIGEVOLVE,
BUT AGUMON AND THE OTHERS
WEREN'T.
DAVIS FROM THE SOCCER CLUB
WENT TO THE DIGITAL WORLD?
THAT'S RIGHT, AND THE TWO KIDS
FROM MY APARTMENT BUILDING --
YOLEE AND CODY --
ALSO GOT NEW DIGIVICES.
IF HEY@HAV DIGIVICES, THAT
MEANS THEY ARE DIIDESTIND.
THAT'S JUST WHAT I THOUGHT.
I
D
EPRR AÃ OE Q
AND MAKING THEM HIS SLAVES,
WILL BIYOMON AND THE OTHERS
BE OKAY?
I
F I GT A -AL ERIR
SHE WAS ASKING
THE SAME QUESTION.
I THINK WE SHOULD
JUST GO THERE
AND DO THINGS OUR WAY.
WE CAN'T. I WENT BACK
TO CHECK THE COMPUTER,
AND THE GATE
WAS ALREADY CLOSED.
THAT MEANS
WE CAN'T HELP THEM?
AND CHECK THE COMPUTER
TO SEE IF THE GATE
HAS OPENED UP AGAIN.
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
AND SO AM I.
M-M.
MM-HMM.
MY BAND'S GOT
A BIG CONCERT COMING UP.
WE HAVE TO PRACTICE.
DONT WORRY ABOUT IT GUYS. JUST
LEAVE EVERYTHING TO US.
OKAY, BUT LET US KNOW
IF YOU NEED US.
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
IT'S STILL CLOSED.
I'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
IZZY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
OH, HI. I WAS TRYING
TO GET MORE INFORMATION
ON WHAT HAPPENED HERE
YESTERDAY.
I COULDN'T SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
I KEPT THINKING ABOUT IT.
IZZY, WILL YOU TAKE ME WITH YOU
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD?
I CAN'T BECAUSE
THE GATE'S NO-- HUH?
LOOK, IT'S OPEN!
HOW'S IT GOING,
GUYS?
HI, EVERYBODY.
THOSE ARE THE NEW DIGIVICES?
HOW COOL.
THOSE WERE RELEASED
FROM THE DIGI-EGG
WHEN I TOUCHED IT.
WHAT ARE WE STANDING
AROUND FOR? LET'S GET GOING.
HOLD IT. I SHOULD GIVE
YOU A COUPLE OF POINTERS
ABOUT THE THINGS
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU'VE ONLY BEEN THERE ONCE.
I THINK WE SHOULD
BE PREPARED FOR DANGER.
MY SUSPICIONS WERE CONFIRMED.
I CHECKED THE OTHER COMPUTERS.
NONE OF THEM SEEMS
TO BE AFFECTED BY THIS.
THE GATE IS ONLY OPEN
ON THIS ONE. THAT'S NOT ALL.
THE GATE HAS NEVER BEEN OPEN
TWO DAYS IN A ROW BEFORE.
THEN I SAY WE GET GOING.
ALL ASHORE
THAT'S GOING ASHORE.
All: MM-HMM.
Man: TAI KAMEA,
IS THAT YOU?
WE HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN A WHILE.
Tai: MR. FUJIAMA.
AND SORA AND IZZY
ARE HERE AS WELL.
DIDN'T YOU ALL GRADUATE?
YEAH, WE DID, AND WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M THE NEW HEAD
OF THE COMPUTER CLUB.
Sora and Tai: BUT WHAT DO
YOU KNOW ABOUT USING COMPUTERS?
NOT A SINGLE THING.
I JUST REMEMBERED
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
YOU GOT A MINUTE?
SURE, WHAT IS IT?
UH, I'VE BEEN HAVING PROBLEMS
ADJUSTING TO HIGH SCHOOL.
IT'S THE GIRLS.
THEY'RE SO MUCH OLDER.
THANKS, TAI. WE OWE YOU.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET GOING.
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-OH ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-O-OH ♪
Izzy: IS EVERYONE OKAY?
Tai: I FEEL LIKE I WENT
THROUGH THE RINSE CYCLE
OF THE DISHWASHER.
WOW, SO THIS IS
THE DIGITAL WORLD. HEY, WAIT.
I'M WEARING DIFFERENT CLOTHES,
AND THEY'RE COMFORTABLE, TOO.
HEY, I'M DRESSED LIKE I'M
PART OF THE COOL CROWD.
I FORGOT ABOUT
A NEW WARDROBE.
I LOVE THIS HELMET. IT MAKES
MY GLASSES LOOK SMALLER.
I WONDER IF THEY HAVE
A SURFER STYLE.
WAIT TILL I TELL MY SISTERS.
KIDS TODAY HAVE NO VALUES.
I SHOWED A LOT MORE RESPECT
WHENEVER I RECEIVED A GIFT.
SORA, I HATE TO SAY THIS.
YOU'RE SOUNDING LIKE MY MOM.
BIYOMON!
TENTOMON!
HA HA HA HA.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU TO GET HERE.
NOW LET THE GAMES BEGIN.
SNIMON, ATTACK!
ARGH!
V-MON, WHERE ARE YOU?
V-MON!
DAVIS!
DAVIS, I'M OVER HERE!
V-MON!
DAVIS. I BROUGHT PATAMON
AND HIS FRIENDS WITH ME.
TENTOMON!
BIYOMON!
TENTOMON.
IZZY, YOU'RE A SIGHT
FOR BIG, GREEN, SORE EYES.
BIYOMON.
I'VE MISSED YOU, SORA.
I'VE MISSED YOU, TOO.
[ GROWLING ]
AAH!
SORA, MOVE!
SPIRAL TWISTER!
BOOM BUBBLE POP!
SUPER SHOCKER!
UHH!
LIGHTNING PAW!
UHH! I'M SORRY,
BUT WITHOUT MY TAIL RING,
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH POWER.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL HAVE TO ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
DAVIS, GET THE EGG READY!
RIGHT!
NOT SO FAST THERE.
THIS IS NOT A DRILL,
DRIMOGEMON.
AAH!
UHH!
[ GROWLS ]
Drimogemon lives
deep inside the cavities
of the digital world.
His drill-spin attack
will make you wish
you were at the dentist.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU'RE UP, MOJYAMON.
[ GROWLS ]
Mojyamon's a frosty digimon
from the snowy mountains.
His bone boomerang attack
will make your head spin.
AAH! BONE BOOMERANG!
WHOA!
V-MON!
UHH.
AAH!
OH, MY. THEY'RE GONE.
THE GROUND JUST OPENED UP
AND SWALLOWED THEM.
WELL, I WANT
TO GO HOME NOW.
FIRST WE HAVE TO PROTECT
OURSELVES.
BUT WHAT ABOUT DAVIS?
[ GROWLS ]
SPIRAL TWISTER!
BOOM BUBBLE POP!
SUPER SHOCKER!
DAVIS WILL BE FINE.
HE'S GOT V-MON.
BUT OUR DIGIMON
ARE ONLY AT HALF-STRENGTH.
WE'VE GOT TO GET AWAY.
[ GROWLS ]
I CAN'T TAKE THIS.
I WANT TO GO HOME.
[ CRYING ]
[ GROANS ]
AAH!
OH, GREAT.
I MUST HAVE BEEN
WALKING IN MY SLEEP AGAIN.
WHE-WHERE AM I?
Digimon Emperor:
YOU'RE JUST HANGING OUT.
WHO ARE YOU?
HA HA HA HA. I'M YOUR WORST
NIGHTMARE COME TO LIFE.
FRANKLY, I'M DISAPPOINTED I WAS
ABLE TO CATCH YOU SO EASILY.
ARE YOU
THE DIGIMON EMPEROR?
SPEAKING.
BUT YOU'RE A KID
JUST LIKE ME.
HA HA HA.
I'M NOTHING LIKE YOU.
IF I WERE, THEN I'D BE THE ONE
HANGING FROM A CLIFF.
OOH, THAT REMINDS ME...
V-MON!
DAVIS!
HEY, GREAT VIEW, ISN'T IT?
I HAVEN'T HAD TIME TO LOOK.
QUICK, ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
UH, JUST ONE PROBLEM...
AREN'T YOU GOING TO NEED THESE
TO PULL OFF THAT LITTLE TRICK?
HA HA HA HA.
AAH!
[ BEEPING ]
WAIT UP. THIS DIGIVICE
YOU WERE NICE ENOUGH TO GIVE ME
IS STARTING TO MAKE NOISE.
MY DIGIVICE
IS GOING OFF, TOO.
I THINK SOMETHING'S NEARBY.
A BUILDING OF SOME SORT.
THERE ARE NO BUILDINGS.
NOPE, JUST THE TEMPLE.
TEMPLE?
IT'S CLOSED DOWN NOW.
Tentomon: TEY COULDN'T BOOK
ENOUGH WEDDINGS OR BARMIT
SOMETHING IN THERE IS MAKING
OUR DIGIVICES GO OFF.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
Yolee: I'M EXHAUSTED. HASN'T
ANYBODY HEARD OF ESCALATORS?
LOOK AT IT THIS WAY, YOLEE.
ONLY A FEW MORE STEPS TO GO.
OHH!
THEY LOOK LIKE DIGI-EGGS.
THAT MUST BE WHT OUR DIGIVICES
HVE BEEN REATING TO.
LOOK, THAT ONE HAS
THE CREST OF LOVE ON IT.
Izzy: AND THAT ONE HAS
THE CREST OF KNOWLEDGE.
[ GRUNTING ]
IT'S JUST NO SE.
WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO MOVE THEM.
I COULDN'T BUDGE
THE DIGI-EGG
WITH THE CREST F COURAGE
ON IT,
BUT SOMEHOW DAVIS MOVED IT
WITH NO PROBLM
HMM.
YOLEE, I THINK YOU
SHOULD TRY TO MOVE IT.
YOU, TOO, CODY.
YOU WANT US
TO TRY IT?
All: [ GASPING ]A
THEY WERE ABLE
TO LIFT THEM.
JUST LIKE DAVIS DID
YESTERDAY.
AAH!
I FEELS SO GOOD TOB OUT
FROM UNDER THT SUFFY ROCK
AND SREAD MYWNS
HOWDY.
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO
WAKE ME UP?
IWS HVING
All0 [ APING ]EAM
GREETINGS.
MY NAME IS HAWKMON,
AND I'VE BEEN WAITING
TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
UH, YOU TALKING TO ME?
[ YAWNS ]
WOWEE. I THINK MY SHELL
FELL ASLEEP.
HI, I'M ARMADIMON,
AND YOU AND I ARE PARTNERS.
UH, WELL...
SO, THEN,YOLEE,
YOU AND I SHALL BE
WORKING TOGETHER AS A TEAM.
WHAT? I DON'T FIGHT
EXCEPT WITH MY SISTER
OVER WHO GETS
THE LAST COOKIE.
ARE YOU SAYING
YOU REFUSE TO FIGHT?
HARUMPH! WHY DO I GET STUCK
WITH A DEFECTIVE HUMAN?
YOLEE.
WHAT IS IT, SORA?
I HAVE THIS FRIEND MIMI,
AND SHE'S A LOT LIKE YOU.
SHE USED TO TELL ME SHE DIDN'T
WANT TO FIGHT ANYMORE EITHER,
EVEN THOUGH SHE KNEW
SHE HAD TO.
SHE DID IT FOR
THE DIGITAL WORLD AND FOR US.
YOLEE, THE MORE YOU DO
TO HELP YOUR DIGIMON,
THE CLOSER THE TWO OF YOU
WILL BECOME,
AND THAT'S A FRIENDSHIP
YOU'LL CARRY WITH YOU
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
AND YOU'VE GOT ANOTHER
FRIEND FOR LIFE, TOO -- ME.
Izzy: SO TELL ME,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD SO FAR?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE ONLY BEEN HERE
FOR A SHORT TIME.
WELL, YOU MUST HAVE
SOME SORT OF OPINION.
I TRY NOT TO MAKE UP MY MIND
UNTIL I HAVE ALL INFORMATION,
BUT THIS PLACE
IS SO NEW TO ME,
I HAVE SO MANY
UNANSWERED QUESTIONS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE TO START FIRST.
YOU SEEM LIKE A KID
WHO WANTS ALL THE FACTS.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE I KNOW.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
DO WHAT I DID --
LEARN TO TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS.
IF THRE'S A PROBLEM
YOU CAN'T SOLVE,
WIL OLVE IT TOGETHER.
OKAY.
I BEG YOUR PARDON,
BUT IN ORDER FOR US
TO ARMOR DIGEVOLV,
YOU MUST SAY,
"DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE."
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
HAWKMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
S ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MON
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
HOLSMON --
THE WINGS OF LOVE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
I AM AN ARMOR DIGIMON.
AS HAWKMON,
IUSE THE DIG-GG OF LOVE
TO ARMO IGEVOLVE.
IUSE MY TEMPEST WING ATTACK
TO DEFEAT MY ENEMIES.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
ARMADIMON
ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
DIGMON --
THE DRILL OF POWER!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
I, TOO, AM AN ARMOR DIGIMON.
AS ARMADIMON,
I USE THE DIGI-EGG OF KOWLEDGE
TO ARMOR DIGEVOLVE.
NOW, WHAT DO
WE GO FIND THE OTHERS?
GIVE ME BACK MY DIGIVICE
TO ARMOR DIAND LET V-MON GO.
HE HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU'VE BOTH BEEN TRESPASSING IN
MY GARDEN WITHOUT MY PERMISSION,
AND AS YOUR PUNISHMENT,
YOU'LL BE FORCED TO WATCH V-MON
AS HE BECOMES MY SLAVE.
V-MON, NO!
HA HA HA HA HA!
YOU'LL NEVER GET ME
TO BE YOUR SLAVE.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
DESTROY ME RIGHT NOW.
AS YOU WISH.
HEY, TAKE IT EASY.
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
COME ON, DON'T YOU KNOW
A GOOD JOKE WHEN YOU HEAR ONE?
A LITTLE COMEDY
TO LIGHTEN THE MOOD.
A FUNNY GUY, V-MON.
COME ON
V-MON, NO!
I DON'T HEAR ANYONE
LAUGHING NOW, V-MON.
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
Holsmon: TEMPEST WING!
WHO'S THAT?
DAVIS, HOLD ON!
SAVE V-MON!
SORRY TO BURST IN
ON YOU LIKE THIS.
YOU COULD HAVE KNOCKED.
GREAT. HMPH!
THIS LITTER BOX AIN'T
BIG ENOUGH FOR THE BOTH OF US.
KEEP YOUR CLAWS TO YOURSELF,
YOU BIG BULLY.
YOU'RE USELESS!
Yolee: THANK YOU!
GRR! HERE, KITTY.
SNIMON!
MOJYAMON!
DRIMOGEMON!
Yolee: HERE YOU GO.
THANKS A LOT, YOLEE.
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR A LITTLE PAYBACK.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, V-MON?
YEAH!
[ Echoes ]
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE!
♪ DIGIMON ♪
V-MON ARMOR DIGEVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ ARMOR DIGEVOLVE ♪
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS ♪
FLADRAMON --
THE FIRE OF COURAGE.
♪ DIGIMON ♪
YOU'D BETTER
HOLD ON TIGHT, YOLEE.
OAY.
LET'S SHOW THEM
WHAT ARMOR DIGIMON CAN DO
AGAINST THE SLAVES
OF THE EMPEROR.
ATTACK!
THE ICE GLOBE!
♪ STARTING TO ACCELERATE ♪
WHEN IT'S FIRE AGAINST ICE,
FIRE ALWAYS WINS.
♪ THIN I'M GETTING DI
TOO MC PINNING♪
UHH!
FIRE ROCKET!
♪ IT'S GETTING TOO INSANE ♪
♪ I'M TRYING ♪
♪ TO MAINTAIN ♪
YEAH, YOU DESTROYED
THE DARK RING, FLADRAMON!
TWIN SICKLES!
AAH!
♪ I RUN AROUND ♪
[ Echoes ]
TIME FOR TEMPEST WING!
♪ YOU RUN AROUND ♪
YOU DID IT, HOLSMON!
♪ WE ALL DO
A RUN, RUN, RUNAROUND ♪
♪ YOU RUN AROUND ♪
I GUESS
WE'RE THE DRILL TEAM.
GOLD RUSH!
♪ YOU RUN AROUND ♪
♪ I RUN AROUND ♪
♪ WE ALL DO
A RUN, RUN, RUNAROUND ♪
HA HA HA HA.
THEY'RE BETTER THAN I THOUGHT.
THIS MAKES THINGS
A LOT MORE INTERESTING.
VMon: SORRY
WE HAD TO FIGHT YOU,
BUT WE HAD TO GET RID
OF THE DARK RINGS.
I'S OKAY.
THANKS FOR SAVING US.
BEING EMPEROR'S SLAVE
WAS THE WORST
IT'S "DESTROY THIS,
DESTROY THAT,
GET ME A CAPPUCCINO." OY!
HE MAKES ME SO MAD!
DIGIMON EMPEROR.
I'LL SHOW HIM
WHO'S IN CHARGE AROUND HERE.
Hawkmon: SETTLE DOWN.
SO, YOLEE, WILL I BE ABLE
TO COUNT ON YOUR ASSISTANCE
FROM NOW ON?
ABSOLUTELY, 100%.
WILL WE BE A TEAM, CODY,
WHEN I'M NOT NAPPING?
I'D BE HONORED
TO BE YOUR PARTNER.
Sora: IT LOOKS LIKE
THE NEW DIGIDESTINED TEAM
DOESN'T NEED US AROUND
ANYMORE.
I STILL THINK WE HAVE
A LOT OF WORK AHEAD.
Biyomon: WE CAN STILL HELP THEM
FIGHT THE EMPEROR.
Tentomon: WE CAN ALSO
PROVIDE ADVICE AND GUIDANCE.
Sora: WHAT A TEAM.
WELL, IT'S TIME
TO GO HOME!
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-OH ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-O-OH ♪
♪ O-OH, O-OH, O-OH ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
THE BIRDS AND THE BEES, HUH?
THANKS, MR. FUJIAMA.
BOY, WHEN IT COMES TO GIRLS,
THIS GUY HAS A LOT TO LEARN.
All: OH!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU GUYS?
All: PLEASE DON'T ASK.
THE NEW DIGIMON RETURNED
TO THEIR IN-TRAINING FORMS.
HUH? UHH!
WOW! HE'S SO CUTE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW THIS LITTLE FELLA
CAN TURN HIMSELF
INTO SUCH A GREAT, BIG CREATURE
LIKE DIGMON.
Kari: ARE WE GOING TO
HAVE TO DO THIS
EVERY TIME WE COME BACK?
Patamon: I THOUGHT
DIGEVOLVING WAS A TOUGH JOB.
Matt: AT LEAST WE MADE IT
BACK SAFE AND SOUND.
Sora: EXCEPT BIYOMON
AND TENTOMON.
We'll both be safe here
because the digimon emperor
never comes out at night.
Imagine -- all that power
and he's afraid of the dark.
WELL, GET SOME REST.
YOU'LL NEED IT FOR TOMORROW.
Davis: WE'LL GO BACK
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND BEAT THAT DIGIMON EMPEROR
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
REALLY? WELL, EXCUSE ME
IF I DON'T START
SHAKING IN MY BOOTS.
WHAT DOES THE DIGIMON EMPEROR
HAVE IN STORE
FOR THE NEW DIGIDESTINED?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."