It was the year 1939.
They appeared all over
the world without warning.
We called them 'Neuroi.'
Nobody knows where they
came from or what they want.
But the hell they brought
drove us all from our countries,
from our cities... they
drove us from our homes.
Mankind came up
with a new weapon
to fight the Neuroi and
began to stand and fight.
The Striker Unit...
a device that heightens
natural magical ability,
the only thing capable
of combating the Neuroi.
This modern witches' broom
made individual flight possible,
but only for a select
few who posses the power.
A call went out to
witches across the world
to lend their
skills to the battle.
This elite task force
organized to fight
the Neuroi was named the
501st Joint Fighter Wing.
But these young women
are known by another name.
Simply called ...
the Strike Witches
There it is...
Climb 15,000 at my
2 o'clock. In the clouds.
Yes, Major...
All units engage the
Neuroi. Formation Bravo.
Strike Witches... Attack, now!
Finish it off.
Copy.
Perrine... You're with me.
Right.
School has ended
for the day girls.
Any students still on campus
should go home at this time.
Don't Yoshika... It's too scary!
Do you want me to
call the teacher?
No... I'm okay.
I can do this.
Yoshika!
That's enough... Get down here!
Not yet...
Just ... a little bit further.
Alright... almost there!
Be careful.
Okay... You're
gonna be alright now.
Yoshika!
Oh, Yoshika!
That was close.
Someone help me!
Hang on... I'll get the teacher.
Did she yell at you?
Well, what's wrong with trying
to save a poor kittens life?
I suppose that's why
I like you so much...
You're always trying
to do things as
if you were
already grown-up...
Grandpa.
Hello!
Michiko!
That's amazing.
I know...
Wow, that ship is huge!
It's got to be the battleship
they said was coming.
Battleship?
Yeah.
A ship that's made only
for war... don't like it.
Because of your father?
He left when I was six...
It's been really
hard without him.
Where are you going Daddy...?
You said that you'd take me to
my first day of school tomorrow.
I'm sorry Yoshika but I've
got important work to do...
If I can succeed we'll finally
defeat the Neuroi... but...
When I'm finished...
I'll never leave you again.
Really...?
You're gonna stay
with me forever?
Yes, I promise.
Yoshika, know that you have
a great power inside of you
just like your mother
and grandmother...
Promise me when you grow up
you'll use that power
to protect everyone.
Okay... I promise.
That was the last time
I ever saw my dad.
What did come back
was his death certificate
and a bag of his
personal effects...
three years later.
They said his
cause of death
was 'classified
military information'
so we never found
out what happened...
One thing I know for sure,
if it weren't for the war,
my dad would be
home with me now.
So that's the girl.
Yes... Yoshika Miyafuji.
She certainly doesn't look
like she's anything special.
Her academics are average...
Her athletic ability is average.
The only place she seems
to excel is... cooking.
Do you really believe
she's our leading candidate?
Major Sakamoto...
What do we do now, huh?
Wait and see...
Michiko!
Hijikata!
Right!
Michiko!
Michiko! Wake up
Oh no! Michiko, no!
Yoshika... please it...
hurts so much.
Don't try to talk!
What's that...?
A healing spell...
one of the most powerful.
She's having
trouble controlling it.
My power...
Calm down Miyafuji...
concentrate.
Relax and breathe into it.
Let the spell do the work.
You are in control of the magic.
I am in control.
Michiko!
She's going to be fine.
Mom...
We've closed the wound and
there shouldn't be any scarring.
Well that's good news.
Apparently you still
haven't figured out
how to control your powers...
Remember your feelings
mustn't control you.
I understand the
youthful impulse
to want to help everyone...
But if you Îdon't learn how
to direct these
energies we possess...
You'll overextend and end
up paying with your life.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted...
I want to learn how to save
people's lives like you two do!
I know that I can do it.
Besides... I made a promise.
Don't lose heart.
Yeah...
Your natural talent
is incredible...
Once you learn how to use it,
there's no way you won't
develop into a great witch.
Wait... A witch?
And just who are you anyway?
Oh, I'm so sorry...
I forgot to introduce myself.
I am a member
of an elite squad,
the 501st Joint Fighter Wing...
Also known as
the Strike Witches...
Major Mio Sakamoto.
Oh, hello.
She's the one who carried you
and Michiko back here
to the clinic, Yoshika.
Carried?
We've been searching
all over the globe
for witches with
great magical potential
and a possible future with us.
I was able to witness
your powers first hand...
They are unfocused
but very powerful.
Thank you.
Now let's say we put
that power of yours
to work for us fighting
against the Neuroi.
Alright... huh?
Hold on!
Are you trying to get my
granddaughter into the military?
Military...? I don't want to...
Thank you but I plan
on taking over this clinic
when I graduate.
Well, taking over this clinic
is certainly a noble idea...
But there are people who
are more in need of your power
than you'll ever
see at this place.
I never expected
you to just say 'yes'
to my offer without
thinking about it, however,
I just know somehow you'll
be coming with me in the end.
And just what makes
you so sure about that?
Hmm? Intuition.
Those with gifts such
as yours are always
led to where their power
is needed the most.
Okay... You can
find me at the port.
Hijikata.
Yes ma'am.
What's her deal...? Really!
They need my power...?
But... if I do what she wants,
I'll be part of that awful war.
Not in a million years!
Mailman!
Coming.
Thank you very much mister!
Mom! Grandma!
How did we get
a letter from dad?
Does this mean that he
really didn't die... huh?
Try to calm down.
It appears to have
been sent from Britannia.
Why is it just showing up now?
Daddy...
There's another one.
Isn't that...?!
It's that woman...
Major Sakamoto.
Somehow the major knew my daddy.
So you're here...
See I told you that
you'd change your mind.
I'm glad you've decided to
come put your power to work.
No, I...
Don't worry...
It'll all be taken care of...
I'll see to it that
your enlistment
and school classes
are my top priority.
Hold on...
You see... I didn't come here
so that you could sign me up.
A letter from Dr. Miyafuji?
That's right...
I wanted to know how
well you knew my dad.
Well...
I do owe him my life.
Your father's
research is the reason
I'm in the position
that I'm in now.
Well then do you know
if my daddy is still alive?
I'm sorry... I don't know
But I will look into it.
You have to take me
along with you to Britannia!
I need to find out what
happened to my dad, please.
Glad to hear it.
Now then...
The ship leaves tomorrow.
Thank you so much!
Okay, now about
your enlistment papers.
Forget it!
I'll never help you
with your war!
Settle down. Okay.
Good bye Yoshika!!
Good luck! Bye!
Michiko, I'll miss you
so much, take care 'kay!
Stay safe dear,
and be sure to write!
Yoshika.
Mama... Grandma...
I'll be back!!
So, enjoying your
time on the Akagi?
Oh um yes...
it's very comfortable.
Good for you...
but you'll only find that
while you're aboard this ship.
I'm sure you've heard what
Britannia is like nowadays...
The Neuroi have taken
over the whole continent.
It's the front line in
our battle against them...
Britannia used to
be so beautiful
Are you only interested
in going there
so you can find your father?
Not just that.
There are a lot of people in
Britannia who need help, right?
Yes... far too many.
Then I... should protect them...
If anybody is wounded
or sick I need to use
these powers of mine to help
them survive as best I can.
I made a promise to my dad.
Major Sakamoto...
Tell me anything
I can do to help.
Cleaning, laundry,
I don't care what it is!
That's the way.
Good girl!
Excuse me.
Check, one, two...
Miyafuji, are you on deck...?
Wait for me there.
I have something
I want to show you.
Show me?
Major Sakamoto...
now commencing
flight training Alpha.
So cool.
Major Sakamoto!
What'd 'ya think?
That was so amazing...!
You were flying around
so fast all over the sky...!
It's like you were a bird!
A bird, huh?
But birds aren't nearly
as fast as we are...
We're part of the
five hundred and first.
We're the Strike Witches!
The Strike Witches.
And our magic broom
is right here.
You are looking
at the Striker Unit.
The invention of...
...None other than Dr. Miyafuji.
My dad invented these?
The invention of the
Striker Unit made it possible
for us to finally fight
back against the Neuroi.
Without your father's invention,
the world would be
completely destroyed by now.
The entire human race
owes Dr. Miyafuji
a deep debt of gratitude.
My father?
Want to try it on?
Your father was the one
who invented it after all ...
It's not going to bite you.
I think I'll pass on it.
I see...
Now I understand the work
that my dad was doing... but...
I won't help with war.
Hey, welcome back!
As usual, the two of you
have a complete
disregard for regulations...
We're on standby alert...
and here you are
wearing next to nothing.
Grow up.
The lieutenant colonel
gave us permission...
Besides, operation says
we won't see another Neuroi
till oh eight hundred...
Or maybe...
Maybe you're frustrated
'cause I'm so tempting.
Yeah.
Or maybe you're mad because no
one wants to see you like that?
That is totally
not true... and besides,
Major Sakamoto is going
to be back any minute now...
I'll be certain to put in my
report how much time
the two of you spent laying
around doing absolutely nothing.
You're so tragic!
Yeah... Especially in the chest.
You just shut your mouth...!
It's not like you have
anything to brag about either.
Neuroi.
It can't be. It's much too soon.
I still can't see it.
Brittania is still about
half a day away at least...
Patience Miyafuji.
But I've already been on
this ship for over a month.
Once we get to Brittania,
we'll go to your dad's address,
and then after that-
What is it?
Neuroi.
Stations!
12 o'clock! Distance 4000!!
Contact confirmed!
This is not a drill.
So, that's a Neuroi.
Miyafuji...
It's too dangerous for
you to be up here now...
Get below deck to the Sick Bay.
I... Okay.
Where's my dad?
The roar of the enemy shook
her young heart to the core;
will she succumb to her
fear or face the enemy...?