Your displeasure is
written all over your face,
calm yourself Major.
They call us all
the way over there
and then start telling us how
the budget is totally fubard;
of course I'm pissed off.
They owe us!
They're just panicking...
We're currently the only ones
consistently getting
results at this point.
They're not going
to see anything other
than what they want
until it's far too late.
That's just how the
warmongers behave.
If the Neuroi had
never shown up,
they would have you, me
and everyone on this team
split into sides and
killing each other instead.
Those damn bankers
think they run the world.
Sorry about that, Miyafuji...
I really wanted to
show around Britannia
so you could know how
beautiful her people can be.
It's okay...
I was actually just
thinking how everyone
in the military
is so different...
Umm... Do you hear something?
That's just Sanya singing.
We're approaching the base.
She came to escort us.
Thanks, Sanya.
Is Sanya really shy?
She just flew away.
She may be a little shy
but she has a pretty voice
and she's a good girl.
Hold on.
What is it, Sanya?
Someone is looking at us.
Someone is what?
Repeat that please.
I'm having trouble
reading your transmission.
I'm sorry.
There is an unknown
bogey inbound
from the direction of
Sirius at high speed.
So is it a Neuroi?
Yes, I believe it's them.
It's speed is too great
to be a normal aircraft.
I don't see anything Sanya...
It's in the clouds.
Target cannot be
acquired visually.
So that's how it is.
Um, Major, what are
we supposed to do?!
Nothing we can do.
We're trapped here.
Without our Striker Units
we're just regular
passengers on this plane.
Do you think they
planned it this way?
The Neuroi aren't capable of
such complicated strategies.
Target is still inbound, fast.
Contact in three minutes.
Sanya... try to buy us
time until backup arrives...
Avoid a direct
engagement if possible.
Yes ma'am.
I'll draw their fire
away from the transport.
Don't do anything reckless.
Watch closely, Miyafuji.
Okay.
Sanya can find Neuroi
even you can't see?
Yes. Her magical
abilities allow her
to see what lies beyond
even the horizon.
Wow...
That's why we always have
her assigned to night patrol...
It's where she makes sense.
It's no different than
your healing magic.
You heard her song, right?
That's one of her spells.
She uses it to
guide the transport.
No return fire.
Just as I thought.
She's able to battle them
before their even visible.
I can't see any Neuroi at all.
You can take
Sanya's word for it.
Sanya, that's enough...
Return to base.
But it's not... I...
Good work.
You were able to
protect us by yourself.
It's raining so hard...
I can't see a thing.
Wait, look over there.
Sanya...
Hold on, Eila!
You can't go alone.
No. She'll be fine.
Looks like it's all over.
So... Nobody actually saw
the Neuroi except Sanya?
It stayed hidden in the clouds
and never showed its face.
'kay... But
I heard it didn't
even bother trying to
shoot back at her...
When does a Neuroi do that?
Are we even certain
it really was a Neuroi?
Maybe it was
a shy Neuroi...
...or maybe not...
Sorry.
No, its true...
Maybe they were connecting
on the same wavelength
like sisters perhaps.
How a Neuroi 'thinks'
is not known...
We need a clearer
picture of their intentions...
Until we have that
there is no way
to predict what
they will do next...
There is a high
likelihood this Neuroi
that failed will return over
and over again till it succeeds.
I agree.
Because of that very reason,
I am going to set up
a special unit specifically
for night missions.
Sanya.
Ma'am.
Miyafuji.
Yeah.
Starting immediately...
The two of you will constitute
the new night combat team.
Are you really sure you want me?
You're the only other one with
experience with this Neroi.
But... I only sat
there and watched.
I'd like to volunteer
for night combat.
That's great...
So Eila makes three total
for the night patrol.
Sorry... this is all because
I let the Neuroi get away.
No! Nobody said that Sanya...
Blueberries?
Why do we have so many... huh?
My uncle shipped
them here all the way
from our farm back home...
Blueberries are supposed to be
really good for your eyesight.
Let's see.
Yes, it's true...
In Brittania all the night
pilots eat blueberries.
It's likely they discovered
their benefits as well.
Yoshika, Shirley!
Stick out your tongues!
Typical.
Perrine!
Everything in moderation.
How could you do
such a thing to me?
Delicious.
You've finished your breakfast.
That's good.
It's time for you
three to go to sleep.
Dismissed.
Huh?
But, we just woke up.
And did they really have to come
and cover up all
of the windows too?
They probably want us
to get used to the dark.
Sorry they turned you room
into such a dark cave Sanya.
They didn't... This is
how I like my room.
Oh, really...
Hey... these are
some type of talisman.
Talisman?
Some people think
they're good luck charms
that scare away ghosts.
People sometimes
mistake me for a ghost.
Yeah...? Because you're
always flying around at night?
Happens a lot during the day...
They say they can't tell
if I'm really there or not.
Don't pay attention to anything
Ms. Priss Four Eyes says.
If you're bored,
I've got Tarot cards.
Tarot cards?
It's fortune telling...
I can use my magic
to see into the future.
I can't see very far though.
Now let's see...
Well. This is good.
You're going to see someone
you've been longing to see.
Is that true...?
It's not...
That's not possible.
Why not?
Because that person
is not coming back.
I see...
I don't know what
to tell you then.
Time to wake up! It's night!
It's dark in here.
They said it's to
help your eyes adjust
to flying during
nighttime missions.
What's this?
It's a special
marigold herbal tea...
I've heard it can
help your eyesight
just as much as blueberries.
Oh really, I heard that that
was just an old wives tale.
What! I've never met such an
insolent brat in all my life.
This secret recipe
is my grandmothers.
Oh... I'm sorry.
This smells like sansho.
Sansho?
Lynne and Yoshika...
Stick out your tongues.
This is so stupid!
Our tongues just look
like normal tongues!
She's got a point.
This isn't a contest!
I was just trying to be helpful!
Yuck
My hands won't stop shaking.
Why?
I didn't think the sky
would actually look
this black at night.
Is this your first
nighttime mission?
Do you want to scrub it?
Will you both hold my hands?
I'm sure I can do it if
you hold my hand, Sanya.
Let's get going.
Wait... I have to... uh...
I'm not ready yet.
Please don't let
go of my hands...
Promise you'll hang on to me!
Wait just another minute...
We're almost above the clouds.
It's beautiful!
I could never have made
it up here on my own.
Sanya. Eila. Thank you!
's okay... It's our job
What's this?
Liver oil... from a lamprey.
It's good for eyesight
and temperament.
It smells kinda fishy.
It's fish oil.
The nutritious benefits
should more than
outweigh the difficult flavor.
Are we back in
kindergarten Yoshika?
What an absurd choice.
Is that so...?
I'm the one who brought it.
I love fish oil!
Ewwww... What's this?
Tastes pretty similar
to engine lubricant.
I was forced to
drink this as a cadet
and I couldn't stand it either.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Another round.
Um... Eila and Sanya,
where are the two of
you from before all this?
I'm from Suomus.
Orussia.
Oh... Where are those again?
Suomus is in the
Northern part of Europe...
Orussia is in the East.
Oh, right...
Wasn't most of Europe destroyed
by the Neuroi in the
first round of attacks?
Yes... the city I lived
in fell a long time ago.
What happened to your family?
When the Neuroi
came they fled the city
and took shelter further east...
much further east...
over the Ural mountains.
Thank goodness for that.
What's so good about that?
Don't you hear
what she's telling you?
Well, they may be
far apart right now
but at least they can get
back together someday.
Orussia is a huge place.
Past the Urals its dozens
of times the size of Fuso.
It's not so easy to find
people once you've lost them.
Besides, there's a Neuroi
hive between here and there.
I see what you mean, but
I'm still a little jealous.
You're kinda
stubborn aren't you?
You don't understand.
What I mean is:
You want to see your
family again, right Sanya?
Yes.
Well, I'll bet they
wake up every morning,
just like you, thinking
and wondering about the day
when you'll all be
reunited as a family.
Yes.
If neither of you ever gives up,
then someday you'll have
to be together again...
It must be so wonderful to
be able to think that way.
I feel so yucky.
Then why don't
we go to the sauna?
Sauna?
C'mon... you've never
been to a sauna before?
Um. Eila This is
getting really boring.
In Suomus we like
saunas more than baths.
Sanya, your skin is so white.
Hey, what are you looking at?
Nothing. She just
has really pretty skin.
Stop looking at Sanya like that!
It's right over here.
You sure this is okay?
Bathing after a sauna is a must.
The water's nice and cold but...
Calm down. It's just
us girls out here.
It's not that... I-
When I hear her...
...her song...
it makes my heart ache.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
Well...
We didn't mean
to interrupt you...
That song. It's so beautiful.
My father.
He wrote that song
for me a long time ago
when I was a little girl.
Your father?
One day many years ago,
when I was little,
I was stuck inside
because of the rain.
I was counting
raindrops out of boredom
and my father turned
it into a song for me.
Sanya went on to
study music in Vienna
at her father's recommendation.
Sounds like a wonderful man.
Your father was a
wonderful man too, Miyafuji.
Huh?
Why's that?
That's easy, because
Dr. Miyafuji was the one
who invented the Striker
Unit that you wear...
That's a special
connection between you.
That's true.
But its not really
the typical present
a father gets for
his little girl.
Don't be so picky...
Those units are expensive.
Hey, guess what?
You'll never guess...
but today is my birthday.
Why didn't you tell us it was?
I usually ignore it
because its also the
day that my father died.
It's a long story and I didn't
want to explain it to everyone.
Well, that's
just plain stupid...
If it's your birthday
then we're obligated
to have some fun, right?
Are you sure about that?
Of course.
Miyafuji.
I want you to listen closely.
Okay.
Hey... I can
hear something.
It's the radio.
At night... the sky is quiet,
so I can pick up radio waves
from distant places
over the horizon.
That's amazing!
I had no idea you could do that!
Yes. It keeps me company
when I'm flying at night.
I thought this
was our little secret.
I'm sorry... but tonight
is a special occasion.
It's your magic.
Do what you want.
What's wrong?
You'll see.
Tonight just also
happens to be...
What?
What is it?
It's a song.
But how could...?
Is this the Neuroi's voice?
It's mimicking
Sanya's frequency...
Where is she?!
According to the schedule,
she's in the middle
of a night training
mission with Sgt. Miyafuji.
Call them back now!
We can't... The song
is blocking our signal.
Dammit! They're after Sanya.
It sounds... like...
Is it the Neuroi, Sanya?
The Neuroi? Where?
You need to leave right now.
Sanya
You idiot! Why fight him alone?
The enemy is after me...
I can feel it.
You have get away from me.
If you're here...
C'mon... what are
you talking about?
We could never do that.
Please go...
You can't see it.
Sanya is going to tell me
where that Neuroi is hiding.
After that...
I'll be able to predict the
enemy's movements short term
with my magic, so I'll be fine.
You are not the same
as that thing Sanya.
It may be alone
but you've got us.
Together we can't be defeated.
Neuroi inbound
from an intersect line
2 degrees off Vega and Altair...
Distance to target
thirty two hundred meters.
Here?
It's accelerating.
A little more lead...
That's good... Three seconds.
Take this!
Did I miss?
No, it's decelerating.
It's sustained heavy damage.
It's coming back.
Oh no you don't!
It dodged it!
Damn it! Show yourself.
It's there!
Eila stop!
Get out of here!
There's no time!
Good thinking Miyafuji.
I've got this...
We're not going
to lose to that thing.
Cause we're a team!
I can still hear it.
Why?
Didn't we destroy it?
No... that's my father's piano.
I see... The radio!
It's reaching to us from
somewhere down there...
Wherever he is...
it's a miracle!
To be expected, really.
Huh?
After all, it is Sanya's
birthday today, too.
Technically, yesterday...
but you know.
It's the same day as mine.
What better way for a father
to celebrate his
daughter's birthday,
than to play the song
he wrote for her...
That kind of love allows
for moments like this,
for those who are
open to feel it...
It's no miracle.
Eila... You're so nice.
No I am not... idiot.
Idiot?
Oh mother... Oh father...
Your daughter is
listening... I'm right here.
A Happy birthday...
right, Sanya?
You too.
I hope you had a Happy
birthday... Miyafuji.
Happy birthday.
Thank you both.
The Neuroi had its
sights on Sanya this time.
It even adapted to her
actions... mimicking them.
It's quite obvious
that we are going to
have start rethinking the way we
approach combat with the Neuroi.
Do you think Command
is aware of any of this?
I don't know...
It's possible they could
know even more than we do.
We can't let our
guard down for a second.
Yoshika's a little twerp
who can get on your nerves.
Shirley's a giant pumpkin
with some super curves.
Lynne is the super ace at
least that's what I think.
Barkhorn's the pretty one
and I'm the one who stinks!