The year is 1944.
Humanity's battle against
the mysterious Neuroi
continued to intensify.
Yoshika Miyafuji
set out for Britannia
with Major Mio Sakamoto
in order to uncover
the mystery of her
father's disappearance.
As their month long
voyage was nearing its end,
the Neuroi attacked.
The 501st Joint Fighter
Wing, The Strike Witches,
is en route from Britannia
to try and rescue the fleet.
All ships break formation
but remain in sections
at maximum operational
speed for evasive action.
Dammit!
Why don't those bastards
hurry up and finish us off?
Maybe they enjoy taking us
apart piece by piece, Captain.
Prepare all fighter
squadrons for takeoff, now...
It's time to show those alien
scum that we're not going
to give up without
a serious fight.
Sir!
Miyafuji!
I won't have that.
Get that fear out of your eyes.
You're at sea now,
young lady, at war.
Sorry...
It's just that... the
shaking doesn't ever stop.
You'll get used to it.
Here... I need you to look
up at me for a minute.
Stay still.
It's an intercom.
Now you'll be able
to communicate to me
whenever you want with
that in your ear, kay?
'kay
However, you should only use it
when its an emergency,
is that understood?
Yes.
Well I should really be getting
back up to the flight deck.
Major Sakamoto?
Um... Are you gonna
fight them... for real?
Of course I am...
I have a duty and
I'm going to honor it.
What do I...?
Should I just...?
You should stay right here.
Don't go outside no
matter what happens.
What if...?
Are you worried something's
going to happen to me...?
Don't be scared.
I'll be just fine.
Restrict 20 mil and
50 cal fire broadside
or abaft the beam
during takeoff.
All hands prepare for launch.
Major Sakamoto...
prepared to launch.
The Destroyer
Yukikaze's been hit.
No response!
Forget it...
All units take off now!
The Neuroi can
regenerate indefinitely
unless their core is destroyed.
All fighters draw their fire
while I search for the core.
Distance to track, 300.
I'm on the ceiling.
Roger!.
There's less defenses up here.
This thing's like a porcupine...
I can't even find an angle
to try and look for the core.
Receiving incoming
flash traffic from Brittania.
"501st Joint Fighter
Wing Dispatched.
ETA to your position,
twenty minutes."
Damn! We're so close.
Order all ships to
continue evasive maneuvers.
Major Sakamoto is out there.
But I'm in here.
Major Sakamoto!
Are you okay... Major!
What are you doing out here?
I told you to stay put,
now get back inside!
Major Sakamoto, I'm so glad
that you haven't been shot down.
Miyafuji, I'm ordering you
to go back inside immediately!
You can't do any good out here.
You're only going
to get in the way.
But I can't stand by
and do nothing.
There is no time for this!
Get back in sick bay before
you get somebody killed.
Major Sakamoto!
Major?! Answer me!
She's a reckless little girl
but she certainly
has a lot of heart.
I better show the same.
The Isokaze's been hit!
Time to finish this.
Wow... that's
how a witch fights.
Found it!
Sakamoto!
Hold on!
I'm going to help you.
Concentrate...
Breathe...
What are you doing?
Back off.
Wait... I was trying to
use some healing magic.
You trying to tell
me you're a witch?
Your powers are weak.
I can do a better
job without your magic.
Stand back.
No...! I have to be able
to do something to help out.
Don't be stupid.
This is a slaughter, kid.
There's no place for you here.
Get back down to sick bay.
I won't go!
There must be
something I can do.
Fine kid... Bandages, okay?
Get as many as you can
carry and bring 'em here.
Got it?
Okay.
Major! We'll try to
buy you some more time.
But just make sure you
find that core, get me?
I'm counting on you.
Godspeed, lieutenants.
Damn it! I'm hit!
You haven't won yet!
All fighters are down
except for Major Sakamoto, sir.
Damn!
Where are our reinforcements?
Can't those Strike Witches
fly here any faster?
That was too close!
The next one will
cripple us for sure.
She just needs to stay afloat
till the cavalry gets here.
Collision bulkhead's
secure but not for long!
IC switchboard's down.
Get a message to
the chief of the boat...
expansion tank is breeched!
Black gang's been blown!
The engine room is flooded!
Use the wardroom
as zero ward for now.
Just get those
bodies out of here!
This is a slaughter kid.
There's no place for you here.
You can't do any good out here.
You're only going
to get in the way.
I guess there's
nothing I can do...
The Akagi!
Miyafuji! Miyafuji!
Come in, Miyafuji...! Miyafuji!
Miyafuji...! Miyafuji!
Yoshika... Yoshika!
Yoshika! Yoshika!
Daddy...
I'm sorry...
I can't do anything.
Yoshika... Know that you have
a great power inside of you,
just like your mother
and grandmother.
Promise me when you grow up,
you'll use that power
to protect everyone.
Daddy...
Direct hit to the
Destroyer Tanikaze!
No response.
Well, looks like
this is finally the end...
Damn... Alright men...
Prepare to abandon ship.
All hands, prepare
to abandon ship.
What's this?
Who gave that authorization?
Captain... there
appears to be someone
operating the central elevator.
What?
I have to do what I can...
...with whatever power I have...
I promised I'd protect everyone.
Who is that?
How can she
equip a Striker Unit?
That's the girl
Major Sakamoto brought.
Her name is...
Yoshika Miyafuji.
Miyafuji...?
As in Dr. Miyafuji?!
Can't be...
Miyafuji?
Let's go!
Pull up...!
You've got to pull up now!
Fly! C'mon!
I'm... I'm flying...!
I can fly!!
I can't believe it...
It's very the first time
she's worn the Striker Unit.
Major Sakamoto!
Hey, where are you going?
I'm here to help.
Look out!
That shield is incredible!
She has more
power than I thought.
Interesting.
Glad to have you on board,
Miyafuji.
Major, I brought
you another gun.
I think you should keep it.
You want to help us, right?
Yes, ma'am!
Excellent.
Let me show you.
Its core is hidden under
the surface right there...
You expose the core...
while I draw its fire.
Think you can?
I'll try and do my best.
Okay
Two seconds... then follow me!
Are you okay?
Yes...
I'm fine... I'm sorry ma'am.
I... I can still fly...
Give me a second.
It's her first flight...
her first battle...
She's had enough.
One more time...
Please let me try!
All right then, get ready,
this could be our
last chance to destroy it.
Right!
If I do it the same
way I'll get hit again...
I have to think.
I see.
I have to stay close to it.
Hold it together, Yoshika.
I can do this.
I'm going to protect everyone.
That's the core!
No... I can't...
Did I... Did I do it?
Unbelievable...
She's had no training...
and she pulled it off.
Core destruction confirmed.
That makes me ten for ten.
Not bad, huh?
Confirmed here as well.
The Neuroi has been
taken out. Good job.
The operation is a success.
Major Sakamoto!
Are you all right?
Perrine always turns into
such a complete suck-up
to the Major after
every battle's over.
I'm going to make sure
to tease her... later on.
I don't believe it!
Who is that and why is
she touching the Major?!
Did I...?
Good to have you back.
Major Sakamoto.
I'm proud of you.
I don't know how much
longer I could have survived
if you hadn't shown
up when you did.
But I was supposed
to destroy the core
and in the end all I did
was shoot around it, right?
What are you talking
about, Miyafuji?
This was only your
first battle, you did great.
Come on... Take a look.
Daddy... I did it... I...
Are you sure this
is the address?
Yes. Until five years ago,
this was Dr. Miyafuji's
development lab
for the Striker Unit...
...up until the day
of the accident.
Major... Did you
know all this before?
I'm sorry.
You don't have
anything to be sorry for.
I'm so grateful that you
brought me all the way here
even though I acted so selfishly
from the moment I met you.
I used to live here
with him a long time ago.
That letter was probably sent
back then and just got lost.
My dad really
has terrible timing...
He left on my
first day of school...
I found out he died
on my tenth birthday...
Suddenly, this letter arrives
and for a second
I thought maybe...
I can see we're supposed
to be father and daughter,
but, I just don't know him.
"Use your power
to protect everyone."
That was one of his
favorite phrases he'd say.
It's why he made the Striker.
He just wanted
to protect everyone.
Daddy.
Shall we get going?
Yes...
Ummm?
Major Sakamoto.
If its still okay I'd like
to join the Strike Witches.
You sure?
I want to stay here and
continue my Father's work.
I want to use my power
to protect everyone I can.
Miyafuji.
I'm sure it's what my father
would have wanted me to do.
I see...
All right, then!
You better get ready.
I'm going to push you until
you turn into real witch,
a true witch!
Are you ready?
Yes.
As of today, the 501st Joint
Fighter Wing has a new member.
Yoshika Miyafuji.
I'm Yoshika Miyafuji!
I'm happy to meet you.
So we have a new recruit.
I wonder what she's like...
I wonder if she's really good...
She could be better than me...
What if she is?
Next time on Strike Witches:
"You're Not Alone."