It seems the
reinforcements and supplies
arrived from Fuso safely.
Yes sir.
Major Sakamoto and a
supplementary member
named Yoshika
Miyafuji have arrived.
As usual, we will be
treating her as a sergeant.
We're certainly thankful
for the increased manpower.
Especially after hearing
that the Neuroi attacks
are becoming
much more irregular.
It's true, sir.
Their intervals seem
to be gradually narrowing
from their usual weekly pattern.
Increasing our
numbers should help.
I doubt we'll be able to
leave things as they are...
With all due respect,
I refuse to have armchair
theories imposed upon us.
All we're asking
for here is results.
And you will have them sir...
Rest assured that Brittania's
skies-along with the rest
of the world's-will be
protected by the Strike Witches.
Oh... that's right...
I joined the Strike Witches.
Sergeant Miyafugi...
How are you today...?
Did you sleep well?
Yes...!
Uh... Major Sakamoto,
do you always train
this early in the morning?
Of course.
And we're both
in the Navy now...
You don't have
to call me "Major."
Yes ma'am...!! Sakamoto, then?
That's better...
This is the front line.
We must always be
prepared for an enemy attack
and train as
often as possible...
It's the key to our survival.
The front line?
Oh come on, don't give
me that scared look...
You definitely have
what it takes...
Our training
together will ensure
that you are ready for anything.
I'm counting on you!
And you can count on me.
Who does she think she is?
She's getting closer
to the Major every day...
That is not okay!
Your attention, please.
Good morning...
Quick announcement...
In case you haven't
gotten to meet her yet,
this is our new recruit.
Major Sakamoto brought her
to us from the Fuso Empire...
This is Yoshika Miyafuji.
Thank you for having me...
I've been looking forward
to meeting all of you.
Miyafuji's rank is Sergeant.
The same rank as you, Lynne,
so would you mind
getting her settled in?
Okay.
Good.
Now, all the documents,
clothing, rank insignia,
and identification
you need are in here.
Excuse me...?
Yes?
I um... I won't
be needing a gun.
Well, I hope not,
but you should keep it
with you in case you do.
Sorry, no thank you.
Right...
She fascinates me.
I don't get it...
What do you think of her?
Huh?
That's... It!
Well, I certainly wasn't
expecting that to happen...
I guess individual introductions
will have to wait 'til later...
You are now dismissed!
So?
Consolation prize.
Lynne's are so much bigger.
You could never
compete with this.
Hi there, my name's
Charlotte Yeager...
I'm a Flight Lieutenant from
the United States of Liberion...
But you can call me Shirley.
Hi...
You need to eat more if
you expect to get bigger.
I'm so bored.
I'm Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen...
Suomus Air Force ensign...
This is Sanya Litvyak,
an Orussia Army lieutenant.
Francesca Lucchini.
Romagna Regia
Aeronautica ensign.
I'm please to meet all of you!
Alright, that's enough
of the introductions...
Time to get ready for duty...
Lynne and Miyafuji will
begin training this afternoon.
Ma'am!
Excellent response
Lynnette...
Begin by showing
Miyafuji around the base.
Yes ma'am, okay.
I'm Yoshika Miyafuji.
Thank you so much
for helping me.
It's my pleasure.
My name's Lynnette Bishop.
So have you memorized the room
locations, Sergeant Miyafuji?
Yeah... Pretty much.
Well, this one's my room.
Here...? No way!
That means we're neighbors!
Oh, is that so?
It looks empty.
Yeah... That's because
I don't have anything yet.
I know a good place
to go for furniture
and other things you might
need--it's kinda far, but...
I'd be happy to take you
if you want to go sometime?
Wow...! Thank you...!
Do you think this place
will have a really
big pot that I can buy...?
Ya'know, For cooking.
Sure... but...
is that all you want?
And this is the
kitchen and dining hall.
Who gets to be on cooking duty?
We have someone
who does it regularly,
but every once in a while,
we let everyone make
their own ethnic cuisines.
Wow...
I could make some really
great stuff with all this.
So I guess you're a
pretty good cook, huh?
I wouldn't say I'm good,
but I like cooking and I like
when people eat what I make.
Who's that?
That's Lieutenant Hartmann...
Her shoot-down count
reached two hundred recently.
Two hundred...?!
Wow, so I guess you
guys have been fighting
the Neuroi for a long time?
Captain Barkhorn--next to her--
shot down two hundred and fifty.
And Commander Minna's count
is over one hundred and sixty...
Without the three of them,
this place would've been
conquered by the
Neuroi a long time ago.
That's incredible!
On top of all that,
they also have special magical
abilities and are protecting
many people's
homelands at the same time.
The Witches are really
amazing, aren't they?
But the only thing I know
how to do is heal people!
At least you can do something...
All I do is slow everyone down.
I can't do anything.
Aw, that's not true.
Come on, let's keep going.
I'm sorry!
It's okay... Silly.
Wow! That's amazing!
This is the highest
point on the entire base.
So the whole island
is the base, then?
Yeah. We're right off
of the Strait of Dover.
It looks really
small from far away.
And...
if you look over there,
you can see Europe.
Unfortunately, the
majority of it has fallen
into the enemy's hands.
It's so quiet here...
and yet, there's a war going on.
You can run faster than that!
Miyafuji!
Tell me what you
see in front of you!
The sea!
Lynnette!
Tell me what's beyond the sea!
Europe is, Ma'am!
And what is the
situation in Europe?!
It's being occupied
by the enemy!
That's right!
It's up to you to
regain that territory!
The only way you're going
to do that is by training!
Got it?! Training!
Training! Training!
Move!
What you need more than magical
strength is physical strength!
Yes Ma'am!
Good...! Give me ten more!
Right!
Miyafuji! Eyes forward!
Ye... Yes Ma'am!
Two more sets!
I can't...
Me... neither!
A little too much to the right.
Pay more attention to the wind.
Yes Ma'am!
Good... nice shot Lynne.
That was amazing...!
Wow I can't even see
the target from here!
I'm sorry.
'kay Miyafuji!
You're up. Get in position!
Next thing we need
to do is get you trained
on the Striker Unit equipment!
Major Sakamoto...
Permission to assist
our new recruits?
Permission granted and
may I say I am impressed.
Good to see you volunteering
your time.
Well... I'm happy to help
and I figured it might be
easier to work in pairs.
Good thinking, Perrine.
I'm Perrine Clostermann,
Lieutenant of the
Gallia Armee de l'Air.
I've been under Major Sakamoto's
care for a very long time now...
You should know
you're very lucky
to have me accompanying you.
Oh yes!
Thank you so much...
I promise to do my best.
Worn out already, Miyafuji?
Well, it's your first day.
That's to be expected...
Though I didn't think your magic
control would be so sloppy...
You need to work on your
baseline stamina too.
And I suggest
you start working on
these things right away.
Otherwise you'll
continue to be a nuisance.
Honestly, I think you'd
be better off going home.
She's a novice, Perrine.
This is her first day...
Don't be so hard on her.
Oh. Right.
Well, there's an
aerial combat technique
I'm trying to perfect
in case of an attack...
I see.
Shall we go up
one more time, then?
Oh yes, I'd love to!
Miyafuji, Lynnette,
that will be all for today.
She doesn't seem to be
showing any improvement.
She's having some
trouble with control,
but her magical powers
are quite strong.
Lynnette's doing
great, isn't she?
I don't know why she can't
do this outside of training.
I would be happy if she did
only half as well in battle.
Agreed.
Good work!
You're done for today!
Captain Barkhorn...
Newbie...
Yes!
Don't you realize
this is the front line?
Your skills in combat
are all that matters here.
Are you prepared to die?
Well... I dunno...
I just really want
to help people.
The Neuroi aren't gonna wait for
you to improve your training...
So if you want to survive...
I suggest you become stronger.
Sergeant Miyafuji?
Hi Lynette!
You um... You found
my favorite spot here.
I did? It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes.
I got in trouble again...
I need to try harder.
I'm a little jealous
of you, Miyafuji.
But why?
Your ability to keep trying
harder and never give up.
Wow.
That's exactly what it
says on my report card!
I don't think there's
anything good anyone
could say about me.
I just don't belong here.
That's not true!
I saw you, you're amazing!
No... I'm not really.
Believe me.
Come on! Yes you are!
Only during training...
During actual
fighting, I'm a failure.
I can't even fly.
But if you can do
it during training...
I know it's hard
for you to believe
'cause you're good at
everything, but I'm not you!
I'm sorry about that.
Lynette, wait!
We've received a report
from the observation post...
It looks like the enemy
has entered the
east grid, sector 114.
Altitude is higher than usual,
to compensate, we'll
be changing formation.
Barkhorn and Hartmann
will be up front...
Shirley and Lucchini
will take the rear.
Perrine, you're with me.
The rest of you will stand
by at the base with me!
Roger!
Wow, look at 'em go!
Yeah, it's great.
Is there anything we can
be doing right now to help?
Maybe you can, but
I would just get in the way.
Where are you going?!
Miyafuji, may I speak
with you for a moment.
Uh... sure...
Britannia is Sergeant Bishop's
homeland so she's sensitive.
You are aware that
Europe has recently fallen
into the hands of
the Neuroi, aren't you?
Yes... Lynnette told me.
That's why this
is so hard for her,
you see, Britannia may
be Europe's last hope.
And... the pressure
becomes too much
for her when defending
it during combat.
I understand.
So what about you?
Why did you decide
to join the Witches?
Me...?
I want to help people who
are in need and protect them.
You know, that's
exactly what Lynne said
when she first enlisted...
Never forget those feelings...
I'm sure your desire to help
everyone will give you strength.
Enemy sighted...! Attack!
That was almost
too easy, wasn't it?
Something isn't right...
I can't seem to find the core.
Do you think it
could be a diversion?
Let's go!
The base is in trouble!
Lynnette?
I um... I'm terrible at magic,
plus I'm always in trouble...
I can't fly... and
I wont use a gun...
What's more...
I don't even care about
fighting against the Neuroi.
I just wanted to
be in the Witches...
I want to be able to use
my magic to help someone...
Even if it's just one person.
But I hope it's not...
Because...
I want to protect everyone.
Protect...?
That's why I keep on trying
and that's why you
should too, Lynnette.
You're saying you and I are the
only ones who can do this...?
But what about Sanya?
She used up all of her magic
during the night patrol...
No good.
Right... Well, it's
just the two of us then.
I want to go, too!
Thank you, Sergeant Miyafuji,
but it's much too
soon for you to fight.
No it's not.
I won't get in anyone's way.
Please, I want to help!
I cannot send someone with
inadequate training into battle.
That would mean certain death.
Not to mention the
fact that you don't even
want to shoot a weapon.
I'll shoot...
to protect someone!
Miyafuji?
None of that matters, Miyafuji.
You're just not ready.
But...
Then I'm going, too!
Lynnette...
If you let us work together,
we'll be just as strong as one.
You have ninety
seconds to get ready.
Roger!
Looks like the enemy will be
approaching from three o' clock.
Eila and I will move on ahead.
You two stay behind
and provide back up, okay?
Right!
Right.
Alright, we're counting on you!
Miyafuji?
I was actually really
scared when we volunteered.
I'm still really scared.
I know this may sound strange,
but I would've been more afraid
if we'd just stayed behind
and not done anything.
That's what I usually do.
What's wrong?
Look over there!
Fast.
This is by far the
fastest one, yet.
Boom and Zoom tactics
aren't going to work...
Prepare to match speed!
Neuroi?
I'm afraid so.
It's coming this way!
It's speeding up.
It's too fast...! This is bad.
I can't do it! I can't hit it!
Yes you can!
It's just like when
you were in training!
It's taking everything
I've got just to fly.
I won't have enough energy
to control my shots with magic.
Fine.
Then I'll support you. Okay.
That way you can just
concentrate on shooting!
What're you doing ...?
Wait!
See...? Don't you
feel more stable?
Um, well, yeah... Thanks.
Bishop, Miyafuji, the enemy
is heading in your direction.
You're the ones we're
counting on at this point.
This is your moment.
Right!
West-northwest wind... velocity
3... and speed... position...
That's it!
If I calculate the
enemy's future position
after evasion and
use that as my target...
When I give you the signal...
I'm gonna need you
to shoot with me!
Okay, you got it!
Shoot now!
Hit it!
Lynnette...! You did it!
Look at that!
Miyafuji!
Did you see that?! I did it!
That's the first time I've
ever been of use to anyone!
And it's all because of you!
Thank you so much!
We're friends aren't we?
You can stop
calling me Miyafuji.
And you can stop
calling me Lynnette.
'Kay. Lynne, right?
Yep... Thanks Yoshika!
I can't... I can't breathe...
My homeland was
overrun by the Neuroi
and eventually went
down in flames...
Now, there is nothing
left for me but to fight...
Even if it means
I fight alone...
Next time on Strike Witches:
"Thanks."