So you're really gonna fly?
True... I've done a lot
of thinking about it...
I'm already twenty...
My powers aren't as strong
as they used to be.
It doesn't matter
how hard I train.
I'm a Witch and in the end,
we all have the same fate.
Hey!
I just don't understand it.
You don't act like
you could be our enemy.
What do you think
you're doing, Miyafuji?
Sakamoto!
Damn you!
Major!
What was that...?!
What happened?
Sakamoto was shot by the Neuroi!
She put up her shield,
but she's hurt pretty badly!
Major, Major!
Major, please be okay.
Please, open your eyes...
Can you hear me...?
Sakamoto, please!
Answer!
Sakamoto!
Major! Can you hear me?!
I'm here...
Everything's gonna be
all right Major, I promise...
Please answer me!
Do something!
Are you okay?
I've got you.
No... It's all my fault!
Sakamoto...
Come on... Please wake up...
You have to...
For me...
Open your eyes... please...
Yoshika!
Let go of me right now...!
I'm fine!
Sergeant Miyafuji, calm down!
Minna...
Major!
Miyafuji!
No, Yoshika...!
Do you need a doctor?
Are you okay?
Can you hear me? Yoshika!
How are you feeling?
Uh... fine...?
You're up at least...
That's good.
Where am I?
Is she gonna be
okay...?! Sakamoto!
What happened to her...?
Answer me, Lynne!
Has there been any improvement?
No.
But it's still too early
to make predictions.
All this is because of you!
Well say something...!
Or are you still waking up
from your damn nap!
She passed out from using all
her power to help Major...
Would you just shut up?!
No, I won't...!
You're not being fair!
Yoshika was trying to help!
And look at how
much good it's done!
Yoshika, wait!
Please wake up.
Have you heard
anything about the Major?
Not yet. We're still waiting.
But in the meantime,
I bought us some food.
Not that again.
Well aren't we picky...?
Shirley...? What will happen...?
Do you think Yoshika'll be
okay after disobeying orders?
What is it?
I'm reading Yoshika's fortune.
Yeah? What did it say?
Says death.
We're dealing with unauthorized
actions and a violation
of orders leading to a
superior getting injured
and the enemy slipping away...
It's a serious offense.
So...
You're saying she should get
court-martialled and shot, huh?
No, that's not what I'm saying!
I know...!
If that were the case
then I'd have been
killed a bunch of times.
Damn it, Erica...
Do you think you could take
this a little more seriously?
Okay...
That's enough, you two...
I'll handle this after
Major Sakamoto wakes up.
Okay!
Don't go too easy on her.
Yoshika, look!
I think we've got a pulse!
Sakamoto!
Major!
Please hang in there!
Can you hear us?!
Be right back...
I'm gonna go get the doctor!
Come on...!
I don't get it,
I'm giving it all I've got.
Oh please...
I'm so scared...
I need help, I wish mom
and grandma were here.
Well, they're not,
so you're just gonna
have to keep trying...!
I'm sorry, It's just you're
the only one who can help...
Please don't
give up, Miyafuji...
Are you listening to me?!
I'm the only one?
You're right...
I am the only one
who can help her now...
I'm not giving up.
Thank you.
I can do this...
just concentrate.
She's gonna be all right.
That's an amazing magical
touch she's got there.
Mio...
Are you... still gonna fly?
Oh... sorry.
You look pale...
You should try to
get some rest yourself.
Thanks again.
Why didn't you shoot?
You know what I'm
talking about, Miyafuji.
Why didn't you shoot the Neuroi?
I just couldn't, I dunno...
Because it was
shaped like a human...?
That was just a
trap to lure you in!
You sure...?
'Cause at the time
it seemed like...
like it really wanted
to be my friend!
It's the enemy...
Not your friend!
Major Sakamoto... You're okay!
Sergeant Yoshika Miyafuji,
in addition to performing
unauthorized actions,
you have ignored
a superior officer...
These are serious offences.
Yes ma'am.
As you know,
I am the only judicial
officer in this squadron...
I'll give you the option...
So, do you wish for a
court-martial to be convened?
I... um...
Alright, from your
lack of response
I will conclude that you do
not wish for a court-martial.
Due to your violation of
orders from a superior...
With the exception
of your duties on base,
daily meals and medical needs...
I'm sentencing you to
ten days of confinement.
Do you object?
No, but...
When the Neuroi
was shaped like a...
I'll ask you again...
Objections?
Please just listen to me!
Do you object?
No ma'am.
Then you're dismissed.
Yoshika, hi!
The major's doing better...
Isn't that great news?
Aren't you happy?
I know...!
Let's take a bath together...!
You're probably drained...
This'll help!
Come on, hurry it up!
'Kay, just a minute.
Here we are!
Over here!
Hey... Yoshika...
I heard you got
confined to your room...
You're lucky.
That could actually be fun!
Yeah and it could've
been a lot worse.
Shirley got the imprisonment
penalty five times!
Hey, what the hell...?
It was four times...
Learn how to count.
I win... Six times!
I have to tell you something...!
It's about the Neuroi...
I think the one that I met
was different from the others.
It was friendly...
It made me think that maybe
not all of them are bad,
maybe we don't have
to fight them at all...
What the hell are
you talking about?
Please calm down.
I'm saying back there it felt
like we understood each other.
Really?
Do you realize what they've
done to us all these years...?
They've done nothing
but terrorize people...
Are you trying to say that
you're on their side now?
I'm just talking about one...!
This one was different!
Do you really think
you've fought enough
of them to make
that distinction?!
I've heard of a
human-shaped one appearing,
but never seen one.
Did it appear at
the Kauhava Base...?
Because that's just a rumor.
But...
Wasn't the singing
Neuroi human shaped?
Who cares?
That whole thing
was just a trap!
Yoshika, this is
supposed to be relaxing...
Cheer up!
Gotcha!
Uh! Francesca stop!
Lucchini!
So do you think
you've gotten any bigger?
No.
Yoshika's aren't big enough yet.
Francesca, why are you
looking at me like that?
Shirley...
Now this is what
I'm talking about!
Wow, I wonder if that's any fun.
No, it's stupid.
What do you think you're doing?!
Hey yours are really
big and soft, Trudy!
These things are completely
useless in combat!
"These things"?
Alright, Miyafuji, this is it...
You may only leave your room
when absolutely necessary.
Why won't anyone believe me...?
It's not fair...
Maybe I was wrong...?
No.
I wonder...
Should I try again?
I have to...
I have to find out for myself.
May I start off
by saying that you
were always way too nice to her.
I mean all you did
was take her in
and let her be a part
of saving the world,
and what does she do?
She turns around
and gets you injured...
I thought I'd lost you.
I mean, I know that
everything's okay now
and you survived...
And I know...
I know it's mostly because
of her magic, but...
Just because I don't
have a power like hers...
doesn't mean that she's...
Perrine!
Sorry.
People told me...
I know that you never left
my side the entire time...
It means a lot...
I'm very grateful.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Yoshika.
Oh, Lynne.
Please don't do this.
If they find out that you left,
you'll get much worse
than confinement!
It's just something
I have to do!
Look...
I don't know anything
about the Neuroi but...
I know you...!
You're someone
who doesn't give up...!
On anything or anyone
you really care about.
That's why...
That's why I'm
going to go with you!
What?
I'm gonna go get ready.
No Lynne...! You can't come!
Why not...?
'Cause I'm not good enough?
No, it's not that...
It's just that I really
think I need to do this alone.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Please promise
you'll come back soon.
I'll be here waiting for you.
Okay.
Sergeant Miyafuji has escaped!
But how?
Impressive.
That idiot...!
What's wrong with her?
I hope headquarters
doesn't find out about this!
We need to bring
her back immediately.
Hello, this is the 501st.
Yes...
But, your Excellency, she's...
No, I understand completely.
Listen up...
Headquarters has commanded
us to shoot down Miyafuji.
I think that's everything...
Perrine, I need you to take care
of the Major
while we're out there.
Right.
Hold on a minute, Lynne.
Yes?
I'm gonna need you to stay here.
It's just for today...
but I'm gonna need
you to stay behind
in confinement
in Yoshika's place.
Right.
What is it with
these witches from Fuso?
Major, are you okay...?
Do you need a doctor?
No, I'm okay...
So this is all because of her?
Yes, it's because
of Yoshika Miayfuji
that the whole base
is in an uproar.
I know...
Perrine, I have a
favor to ask of you.
And, you're the only one
who can help me with this.
Oh... Right!
I think I was around
here somewhere.
Wait!
They're over there.
I can see them!
They're together!
Neuori...
That's the bastard
that shot the Major!
Wait!
What for?!
Look... What is that?
The Neuroi hive.
Cool, I've never
seen that before,
so that's where they come from?
Many of our allies
have attacked it
in order to try and destroy it.
But damn it...
No one's ever been
able to get close enough.
Until now!
Yoshika's going inside!
She's what?!
It's like a
whole hall of clouds!
She just went in.
I don't think anyone's
ever done that before.
It's all part of their trap!
I'm going in!
Get back over here!
I think we should wait awhile.
What... is this?
Is that... the core?
Umm
Is that Earth?
Sakamoto, no!
A Neuroi fragment?
Where... Where is that?!
Are you trying to
play a game with me?
Hey, wait up!
That's me...
She still hasn't come out yet.
Wait, come back!
It's the one from before.
Where's Yoshika?
She's not there. It was a trap!
Everyone, break!
Yes ma'am!
Look!
Hey...! Where did you go?!
What do I do?
I've never seen
beams like this before!
This is bad.
Where's the other one?!
Just what is that thing?!
Is that a...?
It's a beam!
Is that thing a Neuroi, too?
It's really strong.
It took out the
Neuroi in one hit.
What is it?
I don't know.
That beam...
I've never seen power like that.
Yoshika!
Hold on!
Um, Do you think it'll fit?
Yeah, just a little bit further.
Right there. You got it.
Looks like it's started.
Yoshika, are you okay?
Yeah.
Did you see where
the Neuroi went?
Sergeant, Miyafuji...!
You are detained for the
crime of absence without leave!
Return to base!
Hey look, someone's there.
Welcome back, Commander...
Very good work.
It's that thing again.
In the depths of a conspiracy,
the girls' wings are clipped.
Will they ever
break free of the fear
that binds them and
take to the skies again?
Next time on Strike Witches:
"Into the Sky."