Last week the 501st
Joint Fighter Wing,
gained a new
recruit--Yoshika Miyafuji.
Yoshika was paired up with
another rookie, Lynette Bishop,
and the two spent many
arduous days training together.
However, even after
enduring many hardships
with her, Lynnette just
couldn't seem to open up.
She felt embarrassed
of her own shortcomings
and was afraid of what
Yoshika might think.
But during an attack,
the two worked together
and Lynnette attained
her first war achievement,
as well as a new friend.
Chris, no!
Why that dream again...?
Why now?
Yoshika, did you hear...?
They're having Kauhava Base
mobilized for a missing child.
Isn't that wonderful?
I didn't know they did
operations like that here...
That's really cool of them.
And to think, it's
all for just one child.
Of course.
How can we save a country if
we can't help one person...?
It's such a beautiful statement
and makes me proud to be here.
Yeah, I agree.
We can't save everyone...
Doesn't matter what you do.
Someone always gets left behind.
Wait... What do you mean?
Nothing...
I was just talking to myself.
Good morning!
Did everyone sleep ok?
What is this stuff?
That looks fattening
Is there something
wrong, Trudy...?
What's with the
long face this morning?
You haven't even
touched your food.
I have, too.
There was a lot of it.
That's what people
say when they're upset
and don't want to eat...
I know something's wrong now.
What's wrong Yoshika?
Nothing...
I just got a really
weird feeling--
like someone was watching me.
Who do you think it was?
Maybe just my imagination.
I want seconds!
Coming!
Oh no... I'm so sorry.
Did you not like it?
Do I get seconds or not?
Oh, right! Of course
you do! I'm very sorry!
Honestly, I can't say
that I blame her...
I mean you've
served us rotten beans!
No one should have to eat that.
Are you trying to poison us?
Not at all. Sakamoto
said she liked it...
It's just natto. It's
really good for you.
Did you just call the
Major "Sakamoto"...?
You shall address her
as "Major," got it...?
I don't even call
her "Sakamoto...!"
Well, not all the time...
of course... I mean...
Whatever. It doesn't matter...!
I really don't care if
she likes it or not...!
This stuff smells
absolutely horrible
and you should never
ever make it again!
Hey, I'm still hungry!
Okay! I'm sorry!
Wow! That's amazing!
It's Captain Barkhorn
and Lieutenant Hartmann
doing formations.
She's not keeping up.
No, she's a little slow today.
That's so strange.
Barkhorn is usually
such a perfectionist...
Do you think maybe
we should take her off
the next shift so she can rest?
Perhaps, it'll be disconcerting
if we can't use our ace.
I know exactly what you mean...
Even though the others
have gotten better,
we still won't have enough
firepower without her.
I wonder if she's burnt
out from too much training.
I don't think so...
Seems like something
else is bothering her.
Hmm?
I think it has something
to do with Miyafuji.
You sound certain.
I am.
Let's try pairing them up.
You again!
What was that for?!
I'm so sorry!
Here, you can use this.
No, thank you!
So pathetic...
It's like you don't pay
attention to anything.
You're so scattered!
Um... Hi...!
Hello? Sergeant Miyafuji...?!
Turn around when
someone is talking to you!
That's so rude!
I don't get it.
Why am I remembering it now?
Her external
injuries have healed,
but there's no sign that
she will regain consciousness,
perhaps due to shock...
Are you sure?
This city needs
your attention...
Your sister is still
scheduled to leave
with me on the next
boat to Britannia...
You still okay with that?
Yes... Please hurry.
Chris...
I'm so sorry.
Yoshika's late.
I hope she's okay.
I'm here! Sorry I'm late!
What happened?
I was worried about you.
I was cleaning...!
This place is huge!
It took me forever!
I'm sorry... But,
I'm ready to help you now.
What's the matter, Yoshika?
Just thinking...
I get the feeling that
Barkhorn doesn't like me.
Huh...?
Why would you say that?
I dunno.
It just seems like
she's always avoiding me.
Oh don't worry about it...
Captain Barkhorn is
like that to everyone.
It doesn't mean anything.
I take that back.
She's not like that to
Hartmann or the Commander.
How come?
In the beginning it was
just the three of them.
They fought all the
battles by themselves...
They have a bond now.
Wow...
According to the report
from the Operations Room,
we will attack the
day after tomorrow.
Please use today to rest up...
You're certainly going
to need all of your energy
for the coming battle.
Hold on...
Sergeant Miyafuji, Lynette,
don't forget you two
have training after this.
Yes Ma'am...
We promise we'll be there.
Oh gross... She's
completely indecent.
Who me?
She didn't mean that...
But you really shouldn't be
slurping your tea so loudly.
I still don't get it.
What is it about that girl that
Major Sakamoto likes so much?
Alright, what do you want
me to do with it this time?
The same thing
you always do with it.
Nothing's different.
Are you sure?
I really think you should
keep some of it with you.
The only thing I need with me
is food, clothing, and shelter,
and I have that.
Sergeant Miyafuji?
Yes ma'am?
Could you come
here for a minute?
I'm so confused, Lynne.
I just got my salary
from Commander Minna...
I didn't even think
they would be paying me...
I was so surprised.
Why am I not surprised
you're surprised?
The thing that I'm confused
about is the amount.
How much is a pound worth?
Well let's see,
Fuso's currency is um...
It's the yen.
Okay, well then that means
at the recent rate a
pound is kind of like--
One pound is equal
to 19.6 yen right now.
Oh!
Major Sakamoto!
We didn't know you were here!
I noticed.
We should work on that...
You two really need
to be more observant.
Yeah...
19.6 yen is worth
one bagful of rice,
which means ten pounds is...
That means ten pounds is
worth a thousand bowls of rice!
Oh, is that so Miyafuji...?
Then I suggest you
spend your money wisely.
By the way, you've only been
paid for half the month so far.
Really, that was only half?
But major, why are
we getting paid so much?
Simple... we are continuously
standing on the front lines...
Because of that, we never know
when a battle may be
the last one we fight...
Does that make sense?
Yeah, I think so.
They want to make sure
we have proper compensation.
That way we will have no
regrets in the line of fire.
Oh.
They're in the same
bath tub together...?!
How encouraging...
If that's the whole
reason for this money,
then I don't think
I want to keep it.
I understand how you feel,
but I like the thought
of being able to send
something to my family.
You send it home?
Yeah, I have a lot of siblings
and they always
appreciate the extra help.
That's such a
good idea, Lynne...!
I think I'm gonna send mine
to my mom and my grandma.
I bet they could really use it.
Yoshika Miyafuji...!
Can you please explain
how you got to be
such an insensitive
human being?!
Huh?
I've had just about enough
of you, you beastly girl!
First you gave us
gross, disgusting
beans for breakfast...
Then you put a mop in my face...
You slurped
while drinking your tea!
And then you had the nerve
to take a bath with the Major!
You're like some rabid
raccoon-dog mixture!
Raccoon?
Dog mixture, yes!
And if you don't
want to be that,
then how about an
ugly, smelly mongrel?
Why are you so mean to me...?
There's no reason for you
to call me any of
those awful names!
Someone from your land shouldn't
be so chummy with the Major.
What are you talking about?
There's nothing wrong with it.
Sakamoto's from the
same country that I am!
Major Sakamoto...!
How many times do I have to tell
you that before it sinks in?!
She told me not to
call her Major, okay?!
So I'm not going to!
Alright, ladies, that's enough.
Fighting is
strictly prohibited...
You know the rules so I'm gonna
have to punish both of you.
One week of toilet
cleaning should be enough.
Are you gonna respond?
Yes ma'am.
That's more like it...
all right... dismissed.
Dear Mom and Grandma...
I joined the Strike Witches,
but it's been really tough...
My friend Lynne is super
nice to me, but there are still
so many people here that
I can't really talk to yet.
I think... I just...
have to try...harder...
What's the matter...?
Why are you in the dark...?
Let me guess.
You're thinking
about your sister?
I hope you realize
it wasn't your fault.
Course it was...
If we had attacked
the Neuroi sooner
then Chris would never
have gotten involved...
And there's no way anyone could
ever change my mind about that.
Don't you forget we slowed
the enemy's advancement down
and bought time
for people to escape!
It doesn't matter.
The country wasn't protected!
You weren't the only
one responsible for that.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute... you have
a lot of vacation days...
Why don't you take some
time off and go visit her?
I'm sure she'd like to see you.
She doesn't know me anymore...
My life belongs to
the Strike Witches now.
Nothing else matters...
The sister Chris once
knew died that day...
Make sure you put me
on the next mission.
Today we will be focusing
on flight formation...
Lynne will be on my wing.
Yes ma'am!
Barkhorn will be
working with Miyafuji.
Miyafuji. A response, please.
Yes Ma'am!
Wingmen, your only
responsibility today
is to follow your leader...
Should be easy enough.
If she changes direction,
you change direction...
If she tells you
to fire, you fire...
Yes Ma'am
Trust your leader.
She always has her
eye on the enemy...
She will give you specific
orders, so pay attention...
There's never any
reason to question her.
Yes Ma'am
This duel-craft formation is
called a Rotte, and two Rottes
form a Schwarm--which
is also called a flight.
Yes ma'am!
During today's training session,
our unit will be evading
and Barkhorn's unit
will be pursuing us.
Is something wrong, Barkhorn...?
Can't you hear me over there?
Everything's fine...
Let's get moving.
Okay, Lynne, follow me!
Alright, newbie...
Sure hope you're ready.
Right!
That disgusting,
smelly, raccoon-mutt!
What's that?
Incoming!
No way!
Oh no!
It can't be!
It's the Neuroi!
It's entered the east grid,
sector 7, altitude 15,000!
Their attack cycle has
been quite erratic recently.
I heard there was some
activity in Karlsland,
but I don't know all
the details just yet.
Did you say Karlsland?
Something wrong?
No ma'am...
There's nothing wrong.
Alright, prepare
to change formation.
Perrine will now
be Barkhorn's wingman.
Sergeant Miyafuji
will follow my lead.
Let's do this quick
and efficient.
Not again!
Enemy sighted!
Barkhorn unit, move in!
Major, cover them!
I'm right on it...
Miyafuji, follow me!
Right!
I can barely even
keep up with her...
She's flying
right next to her...
that rabid little mongrel!
Something is definitely wrong.
Wrong ma'am?
With Barkhorn, I mean...
She always keeps
her wingman very close
within her field of view.
But for some reason she's
trying to do it all herself.
Hold your aim right there!
Right!
Back up, Barkhorn...!
You're too close!
Captain!
Captain Barkhorn!
Damn it all!
Oh, Captain!
This is all my fault...
What am I gonna do?!
She's bleeding...
We can't move her...
It'll only make it worse.
I'm gonna have to heal her here.
That's okay...
Please, just save her.
stay calm, Yoshika...
You have to concentrate...
You can do this!
Wow that's amazing...
Hold still,
I think it's working.
What do you think you're doing?
You have to get away from me
or you'll put everyone
else in danger...!
Go on, get outta here...!
There is no point in saving me,
so just forget about it.
Use your powers on the enemy,
Hold on...!
I will save you...
We are friends, aren't we?
You're here to
defeat the enemy...
It's my fate to die here.
I don't deserve to live.
That's not true!
You protect people.
If you're not around
then people will die!
I can't do it...
There's no way I can protect
all these people
you're talking about...
I couldn't--I couldn't
even save my sister...
Forget about me...
I'm useless...
Go!
I know it's impossible to
protect everyone Captain,
but I'm still gonna try...!
Because that's what
I came here to do.
I'm not leaving!
I want to help as
many people as I can
and right now you need help!
Hurry...! I can't
fight it off much longer!
Almost done...
Just a little longer...
There...!
Chris...
I don't want to give up...
I have the power to help...
This time I will protect them!
The core!
Captain...
Minna!
What do you think
you're doing...?!
If we lose you, what
are we supposed to do...?!
I understand that
you lost your homeland
and that must be really, really
difficult, but we are a team,
no, a family: you, me,
the entire squad!
Chris is going to get better.
I promise you that...
So for her sake, and for
the sake of your friends,
don't take your
life for granted!
I don't know what
we'd do if you died!
We are the only ones
who can protect our country.
So stop being so
selfish and stay with us!
I'm sorry...
We are a family. You're right.
That vacation you mentioned...
I think I would like
to take it after all...
I'd like to go visit her.
So, I see you finally
decided to do it, huh?
Aw, I didn't even
get to do anything.
C'mon, that's not true.
Yes it is, Lynne, okay?
Well, I suppose
I should thank you.
I figured the least I could do
is express my gratitude.
Sergeant Miyafuji...
I heard all about
the way you saved Trudy!
Trudy?
Captain Barkhorn.
That's her first name.
Oh yeah...
Well I guess you could say
we saved each other, then.
Either way.
I just wanted to say thank you!
Oh look!
I think they're back!
Welcome back!
Captain Barkhorn...!
Your ride is here!
Alright, I'm coming!
Someday...
I'll find a way to repay her.
Thanks.
Tadaa!
What do you think of
my new bathing suit?!
Great if you like showing
off how flat you are!
At least I can see
the ground in front of me!
Besides, I'm still growing!
Next time on Strike Witches...
Fast...!
Big...!
Soft...!