I overslept.
I'm late! I'm late!
My glasses! My glasses.
One, two, three, four,
two, two, three, four...
Shirley... Good morning.
I'm sorry!
What the hell?!
Uh, Sanya...
That's weird...
How did she end up
in the wrong bedroom?
Well... I guess just for today.
Oh great...
So long as she doesn't
go making it a habit.
It's morning! Wake up, Hartmann.
Just five more minutes,
mom... maybe seventy.
I don't think so.
Okay, forty.
Get up!
For a soldier of Karlsland,
discipline, first.
Second, discipline. Third
fourth, fifth is discipline!
Discpline is sixth,
seventh, eighth and ninth!
Discipline.
And tenth?
Do you know what today is?
Hartmann.
Sleep day?
No...! Your commendation
is this afternoon.
In recognition of your
250 kills and service in combat
you are being awarded
the Knights Cross,
with Oak, Leaves, and Swords.
Commander Minna
told you last night.
Can I trade my award for sleep?
You can't! Now get up!
Put on some panties- Pants!
I mean clothes.
Just cover yourself already!
You left this prestigious
medal on the floor?
And you dare to call
yourself a soldier of Karlsland.
It's time for breakfast...
Finish dressing and
meet me in the dining hall.
What...?
They're gone.
Put your hips into it.
Yes, ma'am!
More strength in your top hand
Yes ma'am.
Body and mind are one...
It is not the sword
that defeats the enemy...
Understand Miyafuji?
Not really!
Is that so?
One hundred more swings.
Major, you're so close to her.
Please don't...
I need sword practice, too.
Shouldn't I get special
training sessions with you?
Why does she get
your undivided attention
every morning,
filthy raccoon dog runt.
Hey.
So what are you
looking at Perrine?
Hey, look its
Francesca and Perrine...
Whatcha doin?
I spent all night
up in this tree.
I... uh... hello.
Miyafuji... get back to work.
Oh, right!
Uhhh... me too?
Well... Good idea...! Yes...
You need the training.
Yes!
Lucchini, you too!
Harder! You must train harder!
They're all out
training again...
Major Sakamoto...
She's so very inspiring...
I just hope that
she's not panicking.
No... I'm sorry...
This will be good...
Glad you volunteered.
We needed a guide
familiar with the area...
This is a very important
delivery we're picking up.
I'm happy I could
be of use to you.
No one else is coming down.
Typical...
We're the only disciplined ones.
Well... the Neuroi
won't be attacking today...
It's okay.
You're far too
optimistic, Yankee...
Always be prepared... Right?
So says the Karlsland
girl who can't relax.
I was saving that big one.
Blitzkrieg.
My pants... gone...
Oh well...
Last one in is a rotten egg...
That'll be you, stinky.
Nothing beats a
good soak after training.
Y-yes... You're so right.
Major.
Major?
It's so steamy I can't-
Stupid girls...! Who left
that bar of soap on the floor?
Um are you alright?
I just...
I'm... touching...
can't think... I'm so sorry.
Um ... Is it all right
if I sit with you?
Sure...
Don't be concerned
about rank in the bath.
I'm really sorry, Perrine, 'kay?
The soap just slipped
right out of my hand.
What kind of stupid
orphan raccoon dog...
You could've, killed me...
I mean... thanks so much.
It's a little breezy... Hey.
Hey!
Where are my panties...?
No fair.
Oh no, oh no... this is bad.
Oh my... they're gone...!
Now hold on...
It's not a big deal...
Perrine Clostermann...
Remember to remain calm...
A noble lady of Gallia
must retain her composure
at a time like this.
That's right...
Who cares if
I have no underwear?
It just feels
so uncomfortable...
If I could replace mine...
Those are... the Major's!
But... I can't touch
them without asking...
I... must be mentally insane.
I hear them calling out to me...
Yes... of course... why not...
You can just try them on...
No...! You must
control yourself...
To be caught would be horrible.
Horrible!
I was just...
What are you doing Perrine?
Uhh... Those are mine.
Someone's... been
stealing panties.
It sure is a lovely day.
Indeed... it's
very peaceful here.
A crime... That's for certain.
Can I... have my clothes?
No... This is being
kept as evidence.
But...?
You're not wearing anything...?
Then I'll let you borrow mine.
Wait, no! I'll be fine!
No need to be shy.
Yes there is, please!
Here take my coat...
This should make it better.
Sakamoto... thank you very much!
What turned you into such
a prude...? Strange girl.
Let's start the investigation...
Now who could possibly want
to steal Perrine's underwear?
Maybe she wasn't
wearing any to begin with.
That's absurd.
Of course I was!
We have to assume that
someone has stolen them.
Now... given that...
We need to know who
preceded Officer Clostermann
in the locker room.
It was Ensign
Francesca Lucchini!
Get her!
Those panties are mine!
Wait! Stop!
Wait...! Don't take that!
Come back here!
I'm sorry!
Lucchini! Wait!
Stop!
Slow down.
You're just making things worse!
Delicious!
Which way?
I dunno.
Let's go.
We'll go that way!
Right!
Hey! Lucchini!
No... It rubs...
I can't... without...
Your mine!
No, I'm not.
Francesca... Just give 'em back!
Come on, please.
But why...? You should
come and get them.
Yoshika... I can see you!
Yoshika!
There she is! Stop!
This is stupid!
Don't run!
Eila. Shh!
Oh Please, oh please, oh please.
Perfect!
Hey, wait... I need those!
Crap!
Where is she?
She climbed down.
Go.
Ta-da!
We've got her now!
Justice approaches, you thief.
Nowhere to run!
Give it up!
I'm not a thief!
She's... too... fast!
This is-
The alarm?
It's the Neuroi.
Battle stations.
Right!
'kay, Let's go!
An attack!
Our battle predictions
are completely unreliable...
Better hurry.
I feel so weird...
It just isn't the same fit.
Uh... Sakamoto...
I'm kinda exposed.
And I'm not wearing
anything either.
I don't care...
This is combat girls...!
No one cares about your panties.
I'll go too.
Sanya!
Hey, Eila... you're
wearing my tights.
They're going to
be so mad at me...
I didn't mean to hit the switch.
What switch would that be?
No switch... I didn't... not me
I can't take them off right now!
But those are mine, Eila.
But Major...
It's breezy.
Just deal with it!
Yes ma'am.
Why are you wasting
all this time?
Let's move out... All units!
Ohhh, right.
Everyone stop...
Commander Minna?!!
Commander, the enemy...
Is not here...
It was a false alarm.
Huh?
You can come out, now.
Lucchini!
Francesca!
Lucchini accidentally set off
the alarm when she was hiding.
Also... I've confiscated these.
There they are.
That's a relief.
Excellent work there,
Commander Minna.
Not me...
all of the credit here has
to go Lieutenant Hartmann.
Amidst all the confusion,
she was the one who
retained her composure
and apprehended
the guilty party.
Thank you, ma'am.
Hartmann, I'm so proud of you.
You're the Karlsland
military's finest.
Good job, officer.
Wow! Amazing!
Well...
It's time to begin
the awards ceremony...
That is, of course, if you're
ready...? Lieutenant Hartmann.
Yes, Ma'am.
Lieutenant Hartmann!
Front and Center.
Ma'am.
It's breezy.
Poor Lucchini...
She's cold...
Yeah... but something
doesn't add up.
That's right...
I never would have
taken them if I had mine...
My underwear... was stolen.
What?
Really?
Oh no... there's still a thief
running around the base?
But... who would
steal someone's panties?
She's just trying
to make excuses.
We will now be presenting
one of our highest honors.
Lieutenant Hartman,
in recognition
of your distinguished service
in the field of combat,
it is my honor to bestow
the Knight's Cross
with Oak Leaves and Swords.
Their just
absolutely speechless.
Right.
Congratulations,
Lieutenant Hartmann.
Thank you very much.
Maintaining morale means
maintaining discipline,
no matter how
unreasonable it may seem...
But these girls
are all free spirits
just like I was at their age.
Next time on Strike Witches:
"I Won't Forget You."