Last time, Yoshika was still
having a hard time fitting in.
She fell victim to
Perrine's jealousy.
Then, Barkhorn took out her
traumatic past on Yoshika
by giving her the cold shoulder
and refusing to mentor her.
The tables turned
when the Neuroi attacked
and Yoshika was once
again drawn into battle.
During combat, Captain Barkhorn
was seriously injured by the
Neroi, but survived because
of Yoshika's healing powers.
After that moment,
Yoshika finally felt accepted
by the other members
of her squadron
Wait... What are you doing?
No... Don't... Lynne, come on...
Oh... wow... They're huge...
Yoshika, what's
going on in there?
Are you alright?!
Can you move?
I'm fine... I fell.
I know.
I um... I had a dream about us.
What was it about?
It was nothing!
I don't know! I can't remember!
Isn't it funny how
you can just forget?!
Oh... and I swear,
I didn't see anything.
It's funny...
You never stop working, do you?
What...? Of course I do, silly.
I mean last night.
You were dreaming that we
were in formation together.
Wait? We what...?
Oh... Yeah, that.
You mean training...
That's all we were doing,
just some flying training. Yep.
I know... That's what I mean...
You're training
even in your sleep.
No wonder you're good.
But um, hopefully
after yesterday
you can get some real rest...
We just fought the Neuroi,
so you can forget about
fighting them for a while.
Why did I dream about that...?
It was so weird.
It felt so real...
they felt real...
Lynne's breasts were...
In my dream I could...
Hey! Miyafuji!
It's not what you think!
Are you amused with yourself?
I didn't even see you there!
Me neither! I'm so sorry!
You're slacking.
We're going to the beach?
That's right.
We leave tomorrow morning...
We'll be going to the
eastern coast of this island.
Alright...! The beach...!
I love the sea!
Um... Don't you guys
love the sea, too?
Yoshika...
We're going there
to train... not play.
Oh we are?
That's right, Sergeant!
We have to be
prepared for anything.
And that means
in any location...
For example, what are you
going to do if you lose
your flying capability
out at sea and fall in...?
We'll be training for
those types of situations.
Aw...
What was that, Miyafuji...?!
Do you not want
to train with us?
No! I mean yes!
I want to train! I do!
Okay, I want all of
you to meet us here...
We will be expecting you
at 1000 hours... Clear?
Yes, Commander.
Do you understand the
instructions, Sergeant?
Yes!
Then will you do me a favor
and convey this information
to Shirley and
Ensign Luccini for us...?
Shirley was working
in the hanger
this morning
so look there ...
And Luccini is... She's
probably sleeping somewhere,
so I'd suggest
checking the base.
Right. Got it.
Thank you.
Oh... And there's
one more thing...
I suppose I should tell you,
you won't be training
the entire day...
In other words...
There will be some
down time between drills,
so, pack a swimsuit.
Yes ma'am, I will...
Um, I'll be right back...
Will you come with me
for just a second? Please.
So much energy.
Shirley's in the hanger again?
Yes, since early this morning...
You think she's gonna
come up for air sometime?
It's about to get
noisy around here.
What do you think
I should do about a swimsuit?
You don't have one?
I do, but it's from last year.
I'm worried it
won't fit anymore.
Lucky! So does that
mean you got bigger, then?
Well, Um, yeah...
but not the way you think.
What was that noise?
I think it came from the hanger.
Let's go!
Shirley!
Yo...! What's up you guys?
Getting into trouble?
Um... we thought
we heard something.
Oh... Are you
talking about this.
Now check this out.
Oh wow!
It's really neat! And noisy!
Yep... It's lookin' good...
Maybe I should
adjust the acceleration
on the front a little bit.
Shirley, um... could
you turn it down a bit?
What? I can't hear you.
It's really loud...!
My ears hurt...!
I can't... Can you
please turn it off?!
Are you trying to
blow my ears out?
I'm so sorry!
But... what is this thing
and what are you
doing in the hanger?
You could really hurt yourself.
Why are you guys yelling?
Lucchini!
Did you come in here
just to wake me up
and put me in a bad mood?
'Cause if so, congratulations.
I'm so sorry!
You mean you can
sleep in the hanger
with all this noise around you?
Yeah because that
happens all the time.
It does...?
So does that mean
you're down here a lot?
What are you working on?
I just finished modifying
the Strikers engine.
You modified the
whole engine...?
What does that mean?
I'll be happy
to show you. C'mon.
What does
"modification" mean again?
It means I adjusted the energy
allocation of the magic engine.
And by "allocation" you
mean that you changed
the amount of energy we use
for attacking and defense?
Yep, you got it.
So what part of the engine
did you enhance Shirley?
I enhanced the speed.
Ready!
Right!
Go!
Yeah...! Looks great!
Wow... That was fast!
Oh that's nothing.
That's quite an improvement.
Exactly fifty seconds to reach
an altitude of 1,000 meters.
That is by far her
fastest rate of ascent ever.
It is rather loud, though.
Let's see what
she does this time.
Alright Merlin...
Magical engine, full output, go!
I can't believe she's
still accelerating!
Yep, Seven Hundred and Seventy!
780... 785... 790... 795...
Wow...
800 kilometers!
That's a new record!
Woah!
Go!
Come on let's go... Speed it up.
Her acceleration is peaking.
How fast did she go?
Just a little over
800 kilometers.
I see... So that means she
tops out after reaching 800.
We were right...
It would appear that this
was her limit after all.
The speed of sound.
Still remains just
beyond her reach.
That's amazing!
Shirley! You set a new record!
Alright!
Let's go get something to eat!
What, is all this?
"New Record Achievement
of Glamorous Shirley..."
Um, why are you
in a biker magazine?
I don't know.
I think it's because
she used to ride bikes
before she became a pilot.
Have you ever heard
of the Bonneville Flats?
Bonneville?
Yeah, it's a flat made of salt
as far as the eye can see
right in the middle of Liberion
Wow, I've never heard
of that place before.
I'm not surprised.
It was kinda like a holy
land for us speed freaks.
You could say that
article's the reason
you're graced with
my presence today.
The day it was written,
I was told about these
witches who fly through the air
at the world's fastest
speeds with magical engines.
I went home that day and applied
to enlist in the military.
And now I'm here in a hanger
working with you two ladies.
That's great!
So on your days off you try
to break your speed record
with the equipment
you're working on here?
You have the top speed...!
That's so amazing...!
But if you're
already at the top,
how fast will you have to
go before you're satisfied?
Never thought about it, huh...
The speed of sound...?
I wanna exceed Mach one someday.
Wait... What do you mean
by "the speed of sound."
It's the speed at
which sound travels...
At about
1200 kilometers per hour.
Do you really think it's
possible to go that fast...?
The number sounds
almost made up.
Who knows...? I don't...
But if we don't chase after our
dreams we'll lose them forever.
'Kay, that's all
I've got for today.
Hang on a sec...
You guys came in here
for something, what was it?
Huh?
Oh no we forgot!
We're supposed to meet at
1000 hours tomorrow morning.
How fun! I can't wait!
Oh, to train somewhere else?
To see you two in swim suits!
It's gonna be okay...
I'll just put it back together,
and no one will notice...
Hold on... These two
look exactly alike.
Which one goes on top?
Maybe it was this one...
There. It doesn't
look any different!
I don't think...
My skin is burning.
I'm hungry.
I don't understand?
Why do we have to wear these?!
You'll need them in
a marine emergency.
I don't like repeating
myself, Sergeant.
Alright girls, everyone else
has completed their training...
Looks like you two
are the only ones left.
So stop wasting time
and... get... in... there!
They're not coming up.
Nope.
I guess this means
they won't be flying.
Do you think we're
pushing them too hard?
This isn't the kiddy pool.
Stop dog paddling...!
Take a page out
of Perrine's book!
So sad.
It's heavy...
I can't... Help...!
I'm sleepy.
Okay everyone...!
Time for a break!
I... can't move...
Me neither...
They lied to us Lynnette...
They said we'd have breaks,
but... they still haven't
stopped torturing us.
You get used to it.
Hi, Shirley.
It gets easier... trust me...
And besides you get
to train on the beach...
Nothin' wrong with that.
This feels so good... I love it!
Yeah... me, too!
And me three!
What's that...?
What's the matter?
I dunno... I saw something...
It was flying across the sun.
What was it?
The enemy!
Neuori!
Shirley, hold on!
It's an enemy craft...
It appears to have slipped
through the radar net.
Damn...
The second time it's been
two days ahead of schedule.
Who do we have?
Shirley and the others
are already on the move.
Wow... She even runs fast.
This is Yeager... Taking off.
Shirley, wait!
Are you okay?
We gotta go!
Shirley... Can you hear me?
Yes ma'am!
We've spotted an enemy craft.
An ultra high-speed model...
It's already moving inland.
What is its course?
Current heading, west/northwest
from your location.
Judging by its course...
its target is...
London.
Heading to London!
Single units take the lead!
Shirley, this one's all you.
Show them your speed.
Yes ma'am!
Look how far she is already...!
Lynne, c'mon, we've gotta hurry!
Come on, Shirley...
Please don't, let us down...
Oh no... Shirley's left
the hanger already...
Uh oh.
I really hope I put
it back together right.
You put what back
together right?
Well, um, last night
Shirley's striker was,
I mean, I may or may not have...
Um, nothing... I... forgot.
Are you sure about that...?
I suggest you try to
remember, Ensign Luccini.
What's happening?
Something feels different.
Lieutenant...!
...ust... ...iately...!
I repeat...
Come in Lieutenant...!
You must return to the base...!
I repeat...
Lieutenant Shirley...
Where are they?
Time's running out.
They need to catch up quickly.
She's just getting farther away!
We'll never catch up to her now.
Strange... the acceleration
isn't slowing down...
The engine must be
doing better today.
...to the base... Lieu...
I recognize this feeling...
It's the same...
It's just like that day...
Return to base immediately!
Do you copy?!
Did I do it...?
Did I break Mach 1...?
Is this what supersonic
speed feels like?
Wow...! Awesome!
I did it! I really did it!
Do you copy,
Lieutenant?! Answer me!
Major! I finally did it...!
I exceeded the speed of sound!
Stop! You're going to
crash into the enemy!
Oh no...
The enemy's been destroyed.
What about Shirley?
She's um...
She's... She's fine!
She made it!
Shirley's gonna be okay!
Oh no! She's not gonna be okay!
Oh no I...
What is it?! What happened?!
It's nothing! She's fine Major!
Shirley's been rescued but...
Yeah? But what?!
Wow...! They're gigantic!
Yoshika...! What do
you think you're doing?!
Dammit, Sergeant?!
I demand you tell
me what's going on!
I'm sorry Major!
It's too hard to explain!
I'm so hungry!
Isn't Sanya's voice beautiful?
That's kind of what
the next episode is all
about--Sanya--finally...
Sanya from the left,
Sanya from the right!
It's going to be
the best episode ever!
Next time on Strike Witches:
"We're the Same."