Abandon ship! Abandon ship!
We've got to a life boat.
The ship is going under.
Just run...? There has to
be something we can do!
Don't be stupid!
What can we do
without our Striker Units?
Hold on.
Perrine... help me up.
Major you shouldn't!
We've still got
an ace in the hole.
Right here.
Is that-?
A striker unit!
I'll take off
and try to buy us time
until reinforcements get here.
I want you two to get to safety.
Major...
You can't... No...
Let me go with you.
How Perrine?
There's only one Striker.
But... Major.
Wait Major.
Let me.
It's time I fly.
What are you saying?
That I'm gonna fly!
Sergeant...!
That is not a decision
for you to make!
Fine...!
But I'm not ready to give up!
Who's giving up?
You, if you try
and fly that thing.
You're still too weak to fight!
And if you can't fight
then that means...
It means we're giving up...
And I can't do that...
Not without at least
putting up a fight!
I made a promise to protect you!
You'll protect me...?
I bet you'd be surprised at
how many times I've heard that.
Miyafuji... Prepare to attack!
Right!
What is that?
A carrier... but...
Why is it being
attacked by the Warlock?
Strange that you
think I would know.
Hold on tight!
Holding!
Warlock, ten o' clock...
Altitude... two thousand
meters, right above us.
The right engine sputters
a little at the start,
but don't let that distract you.
Once you get going, you're fine.
Yes ma'am!!
The enemy is here!
Alright, it's time!
Right!
Miyafuji!
Major!
Come on...! You can do it!
Oh, Miyafuji!
Oh no!
Nice work, Perrine!
Thanks!
No way... Is that Miyafuji
fighting the Warlock?!
Hurry, we've got to help her!
Yeah.
I forgot, this thing
doesn't have any weapons.
Here!
Go for it, Miyafuji!
What the? Miyafuji?!
What exactly are you
planning to do with us?
What do you think, Minna?
You certainly have been
keeping busy, haven't you...?
I guess it's not an easy task
deceiving the witches... is it?
The only way for you
to become stronger
than the Witches was
to use Neuroi technology.
You tried to hide your methods
by forcing us to disband...
If we were gone, who else would
even think to question you...?
A decent plan.
However, Sergeant Miyafuji's
actions exceeded military
understandings and
caused you to slip.
I wish...
I wish we had known to trust
Miyafuji's instincts earlier.
Hey! This doesn't look good!
I think the Akagi is sinking!
It looks like the Warlock
is fighting a witch,
but who is it?!
Sergeant Miyafuji!
Are you sure?
Impossible... You don't
have any strikers to use...
Everything is locked away
in the hanger, isn't it?
The signal I'm receiving...
is from Mio's striker.
What? How?!
Not bad at all, Miyafuji!
I've heard to
deceive your enemies...
first deceive your friends.
That sounds just like Sakamoto!
I'm betting Miyafuji's
got her hands full
just trying to buy time...
Let's go!
Yeah, you're right... Come on!
Hey wait!
I don't get it...
Why is the Warlock
attacking the Akagi?
It's just like the Neuroi.
Neuroi...
If it's a Neuroi, then...
Was that a witch I just saw?
Yes.
In fact, she was my friend...
She was the best
friend I've ever had!
No way.
This isn't the Neuroi
that was my friend.
This one...
is the real enemy!
Oh wow.
Yes.
It's amazing that she can hold
her own against that monster.
Alright then...
so we're saying that
when Miyafuji flew up there to
make friends with the Neuroi...
Those guys freaked out on us
and that's the reason
we have to help her fight...
Does that make sense, Minna?
Yep.
Well...? What do you think?
Yeah, sure.
But who are you and
what did you do with Trudy?
Eila! Sanya!
Hi guys, what are you doing?
Is everything okay?
Well, uh... we... um... we...
It's the train's fault!
We fell asleep and
when we woke up,
we were back at
the starting station.
So, ya know, since we're here
we figured we'd see
what was going on...
Right, Sanya?
No... We found out
Yoshika's fighting...
So we... We thought maybe
she could use some help.
Sanya! What's wrong with you!
You're not a very good liar.
I don't think we are, either.
Hey! What do you mean?!
I'm not lying about anything!
Oh c'mon, who cares?
What do you say we get started?
Major...! Keep holding on okay!
I'll be fine... Let go!
No... I'm very sorry Major...
That's one order I won't accept.
Sakamoto!
Okay, Now!
I'm ready, let's go!
Francesca?
Let go!
I can't.
All right!
Nice catch!
Welcome back!
Yeay!
Wait. Please wait
for me, Yoshika.
I'm almost there!
Hi Lynne!
Hey Lynne! We're over here!
You're late...
We'll let it slide this time.
Hurry it up...
You're the last to arrive.
Right...! Yes ma'am!
We did it.
Nice work, Yoshika!
The Akagi...
It's sinking, sir.
Thanks for waiting.
Yoshika!
You're all back!
I'm quite impressed...
Nice work.
Thank you!
Looks like you won't be
needing these anymore, then.
That may not be true.
Look over there.
It can't be.
The Warlock, and the Akagi.
Perrine... Thank you.
'Kay... Letting go.
Don't worry about me.
Wait... Am I seeing things?
The Warlock and the
Akagi have fused together!
It's beyond our
control at this point.
Still... We have to try...
This thing is no longer just
a Warlock or a Neuroi...
It's completely different.
We're not going to give up.
If the witches can't stop it,
then no one else
will be able to!
It's coming.
Alright, listen up...
All units prepare to attack!
Our targets... are the
Akagi and the Warlock!
Right!
The core is in
the Akagi's engine.
I don't think we'll be able
to destroy it from the outside.
Which means we'll
have to go inside.
I'll go. I know my
way around the interior.
No, Major. I'll go!
I'll be her backup!
Well... I know a
little about the inside
and we don't want
you getting lost...
Thank you, Perrine!
Don't thank me...
It's not like this is
some kind of gesture!
Well, it'll be very
comforting for me
to know that you're with them.
Right.
Now...
The rest of us will
provide cover for them
and clear a path so
that they can fly safely.
Roger!
Commence attack!
You're not gonna let the others
take all the credit
for that, are you?
Hey...! Wait!
See ya later!
Sturm!
Hey, that's my job!
Move to the right.
'Kay.
Head upward.
Are you getting sleepy?
I'm okay.
The attacks seem
to be letting up.
So should we go?
Now!
Ready... Go!
Is she okay?
Go for it, Yoshika!
Time for us to go.
Right.
That's the bulkhead.
Yours, Lynne!
Got it!
No, your weapons!
In here.
We're gonna need
more than one gun.
Oh no... But we've
come all this way...
What are you doing?
I was planning on saving this
'till we really needed it...
Tonnerre!
Yoshika.
What are you doing...?
Are you completely crazy?!
Lynne, please... both of you...
I need your help.
Thanks for everything.
They did it.
It's Yoshika!
Yoshika...
You did it!
Yoshika, you're amazing!
I don't know how you
figured that out, but wow!
What's that?
Look at the hive.
It's disappearing!
We won!
Gallia...
My homeland is free...
after all this time.
Amazing...
You're amazing, Yoshika.
So that's it.
Yeah.
Great work, Witches...
All units, return home!
Yes ma'am!
In September of 1944...
The complete
annihilation of the Neuroi
in the Gallia region
was confirmed
and the 501st
Joint Fighter Wing--
the Strike Witches--were
officially disbanded,
but never forgotten.
And to think,
it all started with just
this letter, didn't it?
Yoshika! I need your help!
Michiko! What happened?
I see. I can do this.
Wow... Isn't that amazing!
Yes it is... Thanks!
What's that?
Ow...
A witch!
Hi...
I'm Amaki with the Army Air
Force, Squad forty-seven...
How are you two doing today?
Uh... We're fine.
Do you know Yoshika Miyafuji?
Yeah... I'm Yoshika.
Oh... That's great news!
Huh?
I have a letter for you...
from your dad.