[ASEBI] Come on!
Hurry up, slow poke!
[SAWAGI VP]
No running in the halls.
[SHAGA] Uh-oh.
Sorry 'bout that.
[ASEBI] Yeah,
we won't do it again.
[SAWAGI PRES] Yes,
well, I certainly hope not.
[SAWAGI VP] Let's go.
Whoa,
she got really mad.
Man, we were
just running in the halls,
what's the big
deal about that?
Last one's a rotten egg!
Hey.
Slow down, Asebi!
If you snooze, you lose!
This is gonna hurt really bad!
[SAWAGI PRES] As stewards of
Marutomi University High School,
it is our duty to
exchange students
with other schools
from time to time.
This task falls directly on
the shoulders of the
student council and you,
its distinguished members.
It's almost like we're--
It's like we're diplomats.
And as such,
we'll all have to behave
in a way that does
our school proud.
Yes, indeed.
That's very true, in fact,
you took the words
right out of my mouth.
[SAWAGI VP] With that in mind,
there're many things to discuss.
Direct your attention
to the handout.
The floor is yours, President.
Oh, why, thank you,
Vice-President.
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SHAGA] Take that!
You're in luck, 'cause
I made some incredibly
delicious cookies just for you!
[SATO] Oh, thank yo--
Eat! Eat! Don't they
taste amazingly good?
Eat! Eat!
You're gonna need a
cold glass of milk, huh?
Come on, you silly
goosey you, drink up already!
Hey, Sato.
This game kinda sucks.
I can't reach her
with my punches.
[SATO] That's 'cause
she's a genius at it
and it's pretty much
impossible to beat her.
[SHAGA] Oh, heck yeah!
I'm so awesome at this game!
I bet I could beat
you blind-folded;
you wanna play and see?
Come on.
[ASEBI] Can I play, too?
[YARIZUI] Mm hm.
Aw yeah!
I won!
I'm the winner!
[SATO] Wow, that's surprising;
Asebi's not half bad.
[SHAGA] That's 'cause
she used to work
part time in a game store.
She stunk at first,
but after playing
with the customers every day,
she eventually
got really good at it.
Sato.
[SATO] Yeah?
[SATO] Oh, right.
[VIDEO GAME VOICE]
Excellent! Excellent!
Three times?
Wow! Sucks for you!
[YARIZUI] So.
I'm curious...
How much does the game
and console cost altogether?
[SATO] Oh.
Well.
I'm not sure, but I
know it's pretty cheap
if you buy it second hand.
Why, what's up?
[YARIZUI] Nothing.
I'm just curious, that's all.
[SATO] What are
you doing with my--?
What the hell?
[SATO] Sega!
[SATO]
"Wings", by Yo Sato.
"Wings do not
grant birds freedom.
Some men insist that
to fly through the sky is
the truest freedom
there is, but I disagree.
[SATO] If I were a little bird,
and if my hands and
legs were tiny wings.
I feel certain I would be
missing something very dear.
[SATO] Birds aren't free!"
[OSHIROI] Saito Hiroshi,
more commonly known
as the Muscle Cop,
was cornered by a man who taught
him the hard way
that birds are not free.
When he awoke,
naked and confused,
Saito found himself surrounded
by a mysterious gang.
Though he had fallen from
the sky and smashed into the
ground with a velocity
that should've been fatal,
the great Muscle Cop Saito--
[Sato screams]
[WALLA: STUDENT COUNCIL]
Great job, everyone!
You sound
like a dying seal, Sis.
This is awful!
I'm at my limit, Kyo.
I don't think I can
take it anymore!
[SAWAGI VP] I feel the same.
Trust me. I'm right
there with you, Kyo.
It's bad.
But.
I want to,
but I can't forget her.
No matter how hard
I try, her image keeps
coming back to haunt
me in my dreams.
[beep]
Hey,
take a look at this!
Why, what is it?
Hold on, isn't that
Gabriel Ratchets' Network?
Do we still have
access to that site?
[SAWAGI VP]
Only the bare minimum.
[SAWAGI PRES] Right,
but what are we looking at?
[OSHIROI] Do you want
to watch the birds fly
and feel the cold wind blowing
them across the deep dark night?
The images just keep
popping into my mind!
[MALE MEDIC 8A]
We have an emergency!
Some high schooler
jumped off the fifth floor
of a building to retrieve
his gaming system.
[MALE MEDIC 8B] What?
Hang in there, kid.
We'll patch you up!
Don't worry, you're not
going anywhere 'til
you're as good as new!
[Sawagi Pres moans]
[SAWAGI VP] You're so loud;
would you quiet down?
People need their sleep.
Like me!
[SAWAGI PRES]
You claim to know my heart.
If anyone knows
what makes me tick,
it should be my sister, right?
[BOTH] You and
I are twins, aren't we?
That means you should
know me inside and out.
Yes.
I know your heart.
But even so,
I can't stand it anymore.
[SAWAGI VP] I can't
stand seeing you cry.
And if I'm forced to shed
one more tear myself,
then I might die.
I know you don't want me
to continue on like this.
But I--I must.
No matter what you say,
I am going to do this!
It doesn't matter what you do.
Even if you tore
off my nightgown
leaving me as naked
as the day I was born!
I would still charge ahead
bravely toward my goal!
Come. Please?
[SAWAGI VP] Come where?
What on earth are
you talking about?
I don't understand.
First. We change
into this.
[SAWAGI VP] Um.
No need to worry
your pretty little head,
I have one for you to wear, too.
[SAWAGI VP] If they find us out,
we're gonna be
in some big trouble.
[SAWAGI PRES] We'll be fine.
The map says patients
who are recovering
from surgery are
on the third floor.
K, then let's go.
Hey! Sis! Hide! Get down!
I'm so stressed
out 'cause of all
my medical exams,
I feel like my head's
gonna explode any moment now.
[SAWAGI VP] Will you slow down?
Why are you in such a rush?
I wanna find
the Ice Witch, okay?
You look so cheerful today.
Thanks.
So who was that
young man who
dropped by to visit you earlier?
Your boyfriend?
Gross. No way,
he's just a friend.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Don't be so careless,
are you trying to get us busted?
[SAWAGI VP] I think
we should go head
and find a hideout
somewhere just to be safe.
[SAWAGI PRES] Good call.
Hey, I think I hear
someone coming.
Look.
He's waking up.
[SATO] You guys.
Where am I?
[YARIZUI] The hospital.
[SATO] Hospital?
[SHAGA] Yeah.
The Inoue General Hospital.
It's operated by Asebi's family.
You're pretty
lucky you're not dead.
They said its
better if you stay in
your bed for a little while.
Lie down and rest.
Your whole body's
completely covered
in bandages;
you look like a mummy.
[SHAGA] I'm just really
glad you're still alive.
You fell really far!
Whoosh!
Seeing you like this
has given me an idea
for a role-play that
I think you'll enjoy.
[SATO] A role play?
"Please don't force
yourself on me when I'm all
tied up like this, Shaga!"
Don't look so surprised!
You've got porn mags
in your room with
stuff much worse than that!
I'm no expert,
but don't you have
to be eighteen to
buy dirty magazines?
Oho, he's got his ways!
I bet an innocent, young girl
like the Ice Witch here
would be shocked
if she saw the smut
you've got in your room, Sato.
Or should I say Pervert--
Visiting hours
are over, ladies!
Time to go home!
[SHAGA] 'Kay.
[NURSE 8A] Kids these days.
[SHAGA] Looks like it's
about time for Macchan
to do her job, Ice Witch.
[YARIZUI] Right.
The Ice Witch!
[ASEBI] We'll come
see ya tomorrow!
[SHAGA] Later, Pervert!
--The Beauty by the Lake!
--Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
[SAWAGI PRES]
I'm just a regular nurse!
Hey, hold on.
Why, what's
the matter?
[SHAGA] I feel like I know her.
Huh. Maybe it's
my imagination.
Hey, Sato.
No, please, don't get up.
[SATO] What's up?
Oshiroi found some
inspiration for her novel,
so she left early.
She wanted to write it
down before she lost it.
I'm really sorry, Sato.
I feel horrible.
I didn't realize how
important that thing is to you.
Now that I know, I regret
throwing it out the window.
[YARIZUI] I want
to make it up to you.
[SATO THINKS] I can think of a
couple of things you can do!
I'll let you have
half of my next bento.
[Sato groans]
[YARIZUI] See ya.
[SAWAGI PRES]
I found the Ice Witch!
She's in three-oh-two!
[NURSE 8C] The patient
in room two-oh-six told me
he's suffering from some
pretty bad headaches.
[NURSE 8D] In that case,
it's probably best
to tell a doctor immediately.
I have excellent news!
[SHIRAUME] Ben-To.
[Oshiroi moans]
[OSHIROI] It's wrong.
All wrong.
Well, I suppose
I should get going, huh?
[SAWAGI VP] Not just yet.
What's wrong?
I've made it too
far to tuck my tail
between my legs and give up!
The Ice Witch is
so close I can literally
reach out and touch her.
Stopping now would be
like asking me to take
six steps back and half
a dozen the other way!
[SAWAGI VP] Yes, I know;
but I also know the idiom
you just tried to
use there makes
absolutely no sense whatsoever.
And aren't you
forgetting something?
Oh, that's right.
I took it upon
myself to handle it.
None of this
even matters.
Can't you see it's
entirely meaningless?
Why continue on like this?
Because I want
to meet her for myself!
I want to meet the Ice Witch!
My heart is about to explode,
and I just can't take it!
Oh, Sis.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Don't you worry, Kyo.
I'll come back safe and sound,
just you wait and see!
[SAWAGI VP THINKS] That
night was just like this one.
Why did you come
here again, Sis?
Well?
[SAWAGI PRES]
That girl. Who is she?
[SAWAGI VP] The Ice Witch.
She's an infamous
wolf who
has laid claim to
this territory.
Hold on, how do
you know so much about her?
Because like you,
I find myself intrigued by her.
[SAWAGI VP] Rumor has it,
she's the one who
took out the
Monarch the other day.
[SAWAGI PRES] Seriously?
He used to rule this area!
[SAWAGI VP] She heads up
the strongest club in the west.
The Karasuda High School
Half-Price Food Lover's Club.
In a town of tough competitors,
they're known as the toughest.
[SAWAGI PRES] She must
be something special then.
I'd give anything to see her do
battle up close and in person.
Sis, give me
a status update.
How's it going so far?
Fine. Everything's
in perfect order.
[SAWAGI PRES] It's her.
The Ice Witch.
Sorry! I really
didn't mean to--
I'm just here to
take your temperature.
We want to make sure
we do everything possible
to give you a speedy recovery.
[SAWAGI PRES] I can
take it out in just a second.
[SATO THINKS] I think
I'd rather put it in!
I want to get to know you
as intimately as I possibly can.
[beeping]
[SAWAGI VP]
Ninety-eight-point-four degrees.
That's a little higher
than it should be.
How can you be smart
enough to plan all this out,
and yet still be so completely
clueless about everything else?
[SAWAGI PRES]
I want to know all about you.
Tell me your deepest secrets!
My little heart's
beating so fast.
It's like--
[SAWAGI VP] Like first love.
Isn't that an apt
way to describe it?
[SAWAGI PRES] Yes!
It's like an innocent
and pure first love!
[SAWAGI PRES] Okay,
you can lie back now.
[SATO] What is this?
[SAWAGI PRES] Look at that.
When I put my
feet next to yours--
Your head's all the way up
there and
mine's down here.
Wow. My goodness,
you're really tall.
Well? What should
we do now?
[SAWAGI VP] Sh.
The staff will find us if
you keep yelling like that.
It was a total disaster;
I ruined everything!
Her pulse went nuts and
she started hyperventilating.
There's no doubt about it,
Kyo, the Ice Witch
hates me now for sure.
You can't exactly
blame her; anyone would
get a little weirded out if a
stranger climbed into her bed.
Oh.
You think?
Well, I didn't have a choice!
I'm drawn to her.
And I want to know everything
about her there is to know!
No matter what might happen!
[SATO] Why is she measuring me?
[SAWAGI VP] I need
you to try to stay still.
[SATO] That's weird.
Not sure what, but something
about her is different.
I need to measure
your other arm.
[Sato going crazy]
[SAWAGI VP] Okay, I'm all done.
[SAWAGI PRES] You work fast.
[SAWAGI VP] We good?
We definitely got all
the information we needed.
For a girl, she has
really long arms.
I would imagine her reach
comes in pretty handy
in the middle of a brawl.
[SAWAGI PRES] I wish you
could show me how you move.
There's nothing I'd love more
than to see you in action.
[SAWAGI PRES] I wanna
see what you can do
with those long limbs of yours.
[Sato cries out]
What gives?
Are you okay?
Oh no, please don't tell me.
[SAWAGI PRES] You don't
think I'm worthy of your time!
Go ahead, you can
be honest with me.
Just admit that you think a
round with me would be like--
[SAWAGI VP] Like taking
candy from a baby, perhaps?
[SAWAGI PRES] Yes!
That's the one!
A round with me would be like
giving candy to a little baby!
Oh, boy.
It's taking, not giving;
how does giving candy to
a baby make sense?
[SAWAGI VP] Of all the
people I've ever met,
you're absolutely the worst
at constructing similes.
Seriously, you have got to stop;
it is super embarrassing.
So what? All I want is
to witness the
heroism of the Ice Witch!
I wanna learn her magical ways,
and know all her deepest,
darkest secrets.
Can you explain
how you being a weirdo
stalker has anything to do with
the fact that you're
simile-challenged?
I'm disappointed.
Why weren't you able to
dodge such a weak attack?
[SATO THINKS] Sometimes sweet,
and sometimes sour.
The capricious
nature of a woman.
[SAWAGI VP] She's kind of
muscular, but aside from that,
I really don't
see anything that's
particularly unusual about her.
[SAWAGI PRES] Maybe
there's something at play
that we haven't
thought about yet.
[SAWAGI PRES] That girl.
[SHAGA] Hey!
How ya feelin', sport?
[SAWAGI PRES]
She's a freshman at
Marutomi University High School.
Her name's Ayame Shaga.
[SAWAGI VP] Most people
know her by her nom de guerre,
the Beauty by the Lake.
I have zero good ideas.
I'm thinking about
going for a Hamburg
steak loaded with
garlic chives bento.
Just wait until you see
the size of the patty,
and there's a
crap-ton of rice, too!
Not to mention the
omelet they put on the side!
And the steak comes
on a bed of whole
and chopped cabbage leaves!
Looks great, doesn't it?
And, when I finally
swallow down the last bite,
I promise I'll
be thinking of you.
Bye bye, now!
[SAWAGI PRES] This is
unbelievable, why would the
Ice Witch endure
such humiliation?
[SAWAGI VP] You need to
keep it down out there, Sis.
You're gonna blow our cover.
After everything she said,
how could you
sit there and take it?
I'm so sad.
I could cry!
Because to me you're like.
[Sato shouts with excitement]
[SHAGA] I told him about
the Hamburg steak.
And he seemed pretty jealous.
I just wish I could've
seen the look on his face.
How long will it take
him to recover from that fall?
I bet he'll be
back out tomorrow.
Yeah, but what about
all those bandages?
Oh please, those
are just for show.
[SHAGA] Asebi's family runs that
hospital so I called in a favor.
I asked them to wrap
him up like a mummy
'cause I thought
it'd be hilarious.
[SHAGA] And I was so right.
[SATO THINKS] There's a
hot nurse on top of me,
and I dunno what I should do!
[door opens]
Uh, hi, I'm a nurse.
Okay Sis, you're blowing
your own cover
by completely
freaking out right now.
If I were you,
I'd get outta there ASAP!
[SATO THINKS] What's up
with all the tension?
Oh, no way!
Those two nurses are
about to fight over me!
[SATO THINKS] If I had a choice,
I'd definitely want the
hot one to win!
Roger that, I'm going
to make like a tree
and high tail it out of
here right now.
Excuse me, there are many
pressing matters that
require my attention.
[SATO THINKS] Crap!
The hottie's leaving.
[NURSE 8A] Stop right there.
[SAWAGI PRES]
What can I do for you?
It's your cap.
From now on,
make sure it's on straight.
[SAWAGI PRES] Right.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
[NURSE 8A] Hold on!
What's the matter?
Your collar
is all wrong, too.
[SAWAGI PRES] I'm sorry.
Okay then.
[NURSE 8A] One more thing.
Oh for the love--what
is it now?
[NURSE 8A] Take these.
You're the rookie who started
training here today, aren't you?
Stop slacking and do your job!
[SATO THINKS] No more Grandma.
[SAWAGI VP]
Get outta there, Sis!
Run while you still can!
No way. This is
the perfect opportunity
for me to get some one-on-one
time with the Ice Witch!
[SAWAGI VP] What?
[MOTHER 4] So, what did they
have you cook in home ec. today?
[YOUNG GIRL 4A]
Fish paste rolls!
Want some?
They're delicious!
[MOTHER 4A] Yeah, I can't wait.
[OSHIROI] Maybe
I should go visit Sato.
Come on! Let's get
those clothes off
so I can see everything!
When I first laid
eyes on you, I swear,
it was as if I could
see the fiery passion
burning deep down inside of you.
I will never forget
that moment.
How exciting
and touching it was!
I can't take it!
It's too much!
I can't control myself anymore!
Whoa. It's so muscular;
like a boy's leg.
[SATO] Uh, thank you?
Oh wow,
and your voice is a
lot deeper than I expected.
Yeah, it dropped
after puberty.
What do we have here--
[SAWAGI VP] Oh my.
Oh wow, no way.
You're-- you're a--
Pervert!
Pervert! Pervert!
[SATO] Wait!
He's a big pervert!
[SATO] Wait a sec!
No! Please!
You've got the wrong idea!
[SAWAGI PRES] Somebody
please come and help me!
[SATO] Come back!
I can explain everything!
[SAWAGI PRES]
I'm being chased by a pervert!
[SATO] I'm not a pervert!
I swear to you, I'm not!
[NURSE 8A]
What's this commotion?
[NURSE 8E] We've got a
pervert on our hands, ma'am!
[ASEBI] Hey, guess what?
You're sick,
so I brought you hot milk!
Looky-looky-loo!
[SATO] No. No. No.
Oh no!
[SATO] Okay, that hurt!
I feel like I'm burning alive!
This sucks!
[OSHIROI] Sato?
Holy cow.
This is fappable.
Yes! Momma likey.
[SATO]
'Momma likey' what?
[NURSE 8A] There's the pervert!
I did not see
that one coming.
I mean, who would've
ever thought the
Ice Witch is actually a boy!
No. That wasn't the
Ice Witch, it was Yo Sato,
aka 'The Pervert,' one of
her minions from the club.
The Pervert?
This is dumb!
Why'd we even
dress up like this?
[SAWAGI VP] Hate to
say it, but I told you so.
I even tried to warn you, but
you wouldn't listen to me.
You know, in a way,
I feel like this
experience has
given me some peace.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Truth be told, it's been
three years since my
heart raced like this!
I finally found it.
Oh, hey. What are
those two doing here?
[SHAGA] Bento boxes.
[SHAGA] Whoa!
What happened?
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SAWAGI PRES] Open up and say.
'Ah'!
Are you serious?
Why do I have to do tha--?
Uh-oh, Kyo.
You've got a little
something on your face.
So did I get it?
[SAWAGI PRES] Yeah.
Oh hey, Sis.
Don't worry it's fine.
I already memorized the
entire preview dialogue.
I know it like--
I think 'like the
back of your hand'
is the phrase
you're looking for.
Yes!
I think that's the one!
And yet,
you still haven't said
a single one of
your lines, have you?