[SAWAGI PRES] She's so weak.
I think we might've
got the wrong girl.
[SAWAGI VP] Did you
even look at her?
I mean, her hair and her
build are completely different.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Whatever, details shmetails.
I got too excited to
bother with such things.
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[knock at door]
The door's open.
[SAWAGI PRES] Small group.
Are you the club's only members?
[SHAGA] The class
president and vice president?
There somethin'
I can help you with?
[SAWAGI PRES] It's
considered dreadful manners
to speak with your
mouth full, Shaga.
It's not an action that's very
becoming of the Beauty--
[SAWAGI VP] Just bow.
Oh, yes of course.
It's proper to exchange
pleasantries first.
We're just
dropping by to discuss
a simple matter with you.
I'm sure you're aware of this,
but we still haven't received a
report detailing your club's
activities for last month.
[SHAGA THINKS]
We just played games.
[SAWAGI VP] So is your
club president available?
[SHAGA] Uh.
No, I'm really sorry, but
they're not here right now.
Who is our president?
[SAWAGI PRES] Your club
won't receive any funding
next month unless you get
this turned in right away.
Here, please tell
your president this
is a matter of urgency
and to hand it in ASAP.
Yeah.
[SAWAGI PRES] Now,
the main reason we're here.
[SHAGA] That wasn't
the main reason?
[SAWAGI PRES]
Can you explain what
exactly you're doing
in this photo?
[SHAGA] Um, well.
We'd specifically like
to know under
what pretense you would
visit the grounds of
Karasuda High while
garbed in their uniform.
This is quite
awkward for us.
They are demanding a formal
apology for the incident.
We believe that some form of
explanation is in order here.
It's no big deal; I went
to see Sato and the Ice Witch.
[SAWAGI PRES THINKS] Bingo!
Shaga, you couldn't
possibly be referring to--
I'm sorry, but I'm
afraid we'll have to
request the student
council summon you
for a meeting at a later date.
We'll hear your
formal excuse there.
Sure, whatever.
You don't seem
very well rested.
Not to chastise you, but
the polite course of action
is for one to cover their
mouth whenever they yawn.
You really must take your nom
de guerre into consideration.
You are the Beaut--
[slap and then muffled voice]
[SAWAGI VP] I don't
mean to alarm you,
but there's a hideous
animal in here.
[ASEBI] What?
Really?
I wanna play with a cute
animal! Where'd it go?
[SHAGA] Well, geez.
Talk about stuck up.
C'mere, sweetie!
Whatever.
High five, Shiraume.
And there you have it.
Our first contact with the
Beauty by the Lake.
We need to
tread lightly here.
We still don't know
to what extent these
Wolves are connected
to one another.
I don't think it would
be wise of us to try to
flush them out until we
have more information.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Be honest with me, Kyo.
Did you get the
feeling she thought
I was some kind of weirdo?
[SAWAGI VP] Your act was a
little off, but I'm not worried,
we could've made
a worse impression.
Besides, if she thought
anyone was a weirdo,
I'm pretty sure it was me, which
is still your fault, of course.
[SHAGA] Games, games,
games, games, games.
[SECURITY GUARD] Quit runnin',
you're not gettin' away!
Anyone tryin' to get
close to Shaga's
gonna get their own ass-battery!
[ASEBI] Whoa,
it's like a real life game!
Sounds like Sato's
back on campus again.
[general chaos below and
screeching tires]
[SHAGA] Games, games.
[SHAGA] I guess I
better check on her.
Hang on. Where
did Asebi go?
Well, that makes sense.
[NURSE 10A] Patient Yo Sato?
[SATO] Right here!
[NURSE 10A] We've got
your discharge papers,
so you're ready to go.
We're prescribing some
painkillers, just in case.
Be careful with them, though,
they do cause drowsiness.
[NURSE 10A] Looks
like there's a balance
from your last
examination as well.
So that brings you to a grand
total of ninety-four twenty.
[NURSE 10A] You take care now!
Right, thanks a lot.
This month turned
out to be a bitch.
Well, alright then.
I've got no choice but to score
a big, fat bento the next time--
Orthros?
Are you serious?
This guy must
be incredibly strong.
To say the least.
And they've been popping
up a lot these past few days,
randomly taking down
eastern wolves left and right.
[NIKAIDO] Every Wolf
needs to be aware of this.
[SHAGA] So, what?
You're trying to
figure out who he is?
[NIKAIDO] If possible.
It's gotten to the
point where none of the
Eastern Wolves are
willing to fight them.
Every person who's faced
Orthros is now racked with
fear and they've completely
lost their taste for battle.
Some of them would rather starve
than go to another bento brawl.
[SHAGA] Okay, but if
he's fought that many Wolves,
all you gotta do is ask
one of them what he
looks like and you can
figure out the rest, right?
[NIKAIDO] It'd be great
if it were that easy,
but none of Orthros'
victims are exactly helpful;
they all said the same thing
when I asked them about it.
"The next thing I knew,
I was plunged into darkness."
[NIKAIDO] In other words,
nobody can remember.
We've got no idea what Orthros
look like or how they fight.
There's only one
thing we do know,
Orthros is the nom de
guerre for a pack of two.
Wait, a pack?
So, you're saying
Orthros is two people?
[NIKAIDO] Yeah, according
to the one person
with some memory of their
attack, a Karasuda student who
went to a brawl in the East,
she was the last
victim I spoke with.
[NIKAIDO] And she
heard something
before she blacked out.
[SAWAGI PRES] I think we
might've got the wrong girl.
[SHAGA] The wrong girl?
[NIKAIDO] And she had a
theory on why they said that.
She said she's convinced Orthros
is searching for a particular
Wolf whom they feel will
be a worthy opponent.
[SHAGA] Why?
What do they want?
Did you just
say the Monarch?
[SATO] Yeah, all splayed out
in a store on the Eastside.
I was kinda wonderin' if
you were the one behind it.
And why the hell
would I do something like that?
Dammit!
So, hey, I was thinking.
[SATO] Oh, yeah?
Were you still
planning to go
to a bento brawl tomorrow night?
[SATO] Mm-hmm.
Why don't you
go to a supermarket
on the Eastside for a change?
[SATO] Nope.
Yarizui made a good point.
[YARIZUI] Y'know, Sato.
If you wanna get
back to bento brawling,
I think you should hit
up the Kamoshida Mart.
There aren't any
high schools in that area,
so your competition
should be light.
It won't mess with
your healing too much.
You should take it easy
until you're a hundred percent.
That okay?
And that's
what I'm doing.
It kinda sounded like she
might be worried about me.
So it's the Kamoshida
Mart for me until--
What?
No way!
Bow before
your master, swine.
[SATO] One more round!
[SHAGA] Alright, drop dead.
[Sato cries out]
[SHAGA] How'd ya like that?
Ninety-four victories,
three hundred-seventy-eight
losses. Good morning.
You got somethin'
on your mind, Oshiroi?
[OSHIROI] Maybe if
Saito was actually a decoy.
No, that's such a cliché.
But a naked investigation,
now that's original.
Maybe at a hot spring,
no, a changing room.
[SATO] Ugh.
Freakin' creepy.
[OSHIROI] And once
all of Saito's openings
had been stuffed full--
wait, no, the lockers.
I mean the lockers.
Once Saito had been fully
stuffed inside the locker.
[YARIZUI] Sato.
You gonna make your move?
[SATO] Right.
Sorry.
You're brawling tonight.
Give it your all.
Oh, I'm planning on it.
It's been too long since
I had half-price-- Hey!
Can I please take
back that last move?
[YARIZUI] Of course not.
[OSHIROI] I'll see
you guys later, okay?
I'm gonna skip tonight's
brawl and head home.
But best of luck
to the two of you!
[OSHIROI] Two!
Of course, that's it!
There are two of them!
Geez, I can't believe it took
me this long to realize it!
Two people are attacking Saito!
Hold on, are you gonna
fight two people this time?
[SHAGA] Huh.
So this is Kamoshida.
[SHAGA] Whoa.
What?
Why are they here?
[SHAGA] I'm gonna
have to hear their crap:
"Fighting for half-price
food is so gauche".
They're so damn stuck up.
[SHAGA] Well, I doubt
we've gotta worry about
Orthros showing up at
a tiny store like this.
Good luck, Sato!
And the rush
is starting to kick in.
I missed this feeling.
Yarizui.
I'm not sure if your logic was
entirely sound on this strategy.
It looks like there're plenty
of hungry Wolves after all.
Now what should I go for?
[SAWAGI PRES AND SAWAGI VP]
Well, look who it is.
[SATO] I know you.
Huh?
It's nice to see you again.
How are you, Pervert?
[SHAGA] What the hell?
Oh no, Sato!
[SAWAGI VP] Ben-
[SAWAGI PRES] To!
You're finally awake.
You shouldn't
try to talk yet.
It looks like Orthros pulled
a serious number on you.
I'll explain.
Orthros is a pack of two Wolves
who recently
appeared on the scene.
The Beauty by the Lake can fill
in some of the details for you,
but in all honestly, we really
don't know that much about 'em.
I'm guessing you don't
remember anything either.
Then there's
no doubt they're
the ones who attacked you.
And seems they've targeted
the Half-Price Food Lovers Club.
I have a feeling
I know who's next.
[SHAGA] Chill!
[NIKAIDO] You earned that one.
Call me if you
remember anything.
[Sawagi Pres cries
and blows bubbles]
Can you please
not drown yourself, Sis?
What's your problem this time?
[SAWAGI PRES] What do you think?
The Pervert was so much
weaker than his reputation.
[SAWAGI VP] I know how you feel.
I simply can't believe he's the
one who took down the Monarch.
It's quite disappointing.
[SAWAGI PRES] I just wasn't
expecting him to be so pitiful.
Maybe I was a little
too rough on him.
We should apologize
next time we see him.
[SAWAGI VP] They're not
supposed to remember us,
Kyo, so just walking right
up and apologizing
for attacking them might
defeat the purpose.
I feel completely
unfulfilled from that fight.
I've gotta scratch
this itch, Kyo!
I say we hit every store around
Karasuda High starting tomorrow!
[SAWAGI VP] You've gotta
get a grip on yourself, Sis.
We can't draw
that much attention.
The last thing we need
is for them to expect us.
[SAWAGI PRES] But there's
no way we can stop now.
We promised we would
never surrender again.
Not after what happened.
[SAWAGI VP] I know that we can't
but there's just
so much at stake.
I don't think I
could live through
that kind of humiliation again.
Once was too much.
I'd rather die.
[SATO] Oh, my head.
[SATO] Greek mythology?
Interesting.
Orthros, that sounds--
I'll explain. Orthros
is a pack of two Wolves
who recently appeared
on the scene.
[SATO] Orthros is a bicephal.
A large two-headed black dog,
brother of Cerberus,
the guard dog of Hades.
Orthros was
charged with guarding a
herd as opposed
to the gates of Hell.
He was killed by
Heracles during a
raid to steal the red cattle.
A tragic end for a
loyal and skilled herding dog.
[NIKAIDO] I have a feeling
I know who's next.
[SATO] Sorry, I didn't
mean to wake you.
Geez, I can't believe
I fell asleep like that.
So uh, what's this?
Not to pry or anything.
[YARIZUI]
Oshiroi was looking at it.
I guess she was using it as
a reference for her novel.
I passed out before she left,
she must've forgotten it.
Man.
She really does a lot of work on
those creepy novels of hers.
[YARIZUI] Why is your
face all bandaged up?
Well, I got the
crap kicked outta me.
[YARIZUI] I take it that's why
you didn't come back last night?
[SATO] Yeah, sorry about that.
[YARIZUI] There's no
need to apologize,
I know you didn't
do it on purpose.
Just keep working on
building your health back up.
[SATO] Yeah!
I am!
Funny coincidence
about this book,
the one who attacked me--
I was just thinking.
Uh, yeah?
You know,
about tonight?
Why don't you
come with me?
Wait.
Come with you?
I think we should
do it together.
[SATO] You think we should?
[YARIZUI] Well, yeah.
After last night, you
should come along with me.
Yeah, you're
absolutely right!
As long as you're sure--
Great, we'll walk to
the market together then.
You need to celebrate now that
you're out of the hospital.
What better way
than half-price food?
[SATO] Sounds good.
I'm sure we'll
be fine tonight.
Did you say
something to me?
[SATO] Oh,
it was nothing; forget it.
[SATO THINKS] The odds of
running into Orthros two
nights in a row
have gotta be pretty slim.
[SATO] Shaga?
Hey.
[YARIZUI] I'll be
waiting over by the bento.
So what's up, what're
you doing out here?
[SHAGA] No reason.
I just felt like it.
[GOATEE] Hey.
Pervert.
It's nice you're
out of the hospital and all,
but don't expect us to go
easy on you or anything.
We'll celebrate your discharge
by letting you watch us win.
[SATO] Hey.
[BRUNETTE] What?
[SATO]
Your head, are you okay?
[BRUNETTE] It's nothin',
just a few scratches.
[MONK] It could've
been a lot worse
but she passed out
after the first punch.
Whoa!
What the hell?
[SHAGA] Hey!
[SATO] Good evening ladies!
Thanks!
Good evening to you too!
Y'know, this feels
familiar somehow.
Are you guys--are you twins?
We would like
to apologize to you.
We got a little carried
away yesterday.
I don't know why
you're apologizing, but okay.
I'm so glad we got
the chance to see you again.
[SATO] Yeah, me too,
I'm twice as glad.
I feel like I'm at a buy-one
get-one free sale.
Oh my goodness,
how rude of us,
I just realized we haven't
even introduced ourselves yet.
My name is Kyo Sawagi.
And this is my
little sister, Kyo.
[SATO] Wait.
Kyo and Kyo?
Yes.
It's pronounced the same
but the character is different.
See, my 'Kyo' is the one
in myocardial infarction and--
Her 'Kyo' is the one in
bellflower and my
'Kyo' is the one in mirror.
[SAWAGI PRES] Exactly,
that's what I meant.
Don't forget it
when you see us again.
Always a pleasure to
see you, Beauty by the Lake.
What's with you?
Is something wrong?
[BRUNETTE] No.
I guess not.
"It's warm and gentle.
A flavor I remember from long
ago at my Grandmother's.
A Japanese dish easy on
both mind and body.
Plum and dried
sardines over rice,
served with seasonal
vegetables." It's mine.
Freaking long name.
I was starting to
get worried you
were having a
stroke or somethin'.
But that's just your meal.
I'm gonna shoot
for the shrimp tempura.
Pervert!
Look out!
Whoa, Shaga!
[YARIZUI] What the--?
What the hell
is goin' on here?
[YARIZUI] Sato!
Look!
Ice Witch!
Be careful!
Watch out for the basket!
[SAWAGI PRES] The Ice Witch?
[SAWAGI PRES] We've found you!
At long last, we finally meet!
This moment's
been a long time coming.
If only you could
know how eagerly
we've anticipated
meeting you in battle.
Make it count, Ice Witch.
Holy-- Look at that!
They're using the
baskets for their attacks!
[SATO] I see.
So they're the ones.
[SHAGA] They're Orthros!
What?
Orthros?
[SHAGA] Bring it on!
Nice try, Beauty.
But you're weaker
than you realize.
[NIKAIDO] I'm putting
you down, Orthros!
[SAWAGI VP] Sure,
you might have led the
Gabriel Ratchet
back in your day.
[SAWAGI PRES] But your
time has come and gone!
[SAWAGI VP]
Is this all you've got?
[SAWAGI PRES] You're
disappointing us, Witch!
[SATO] You got 'em!
[SAWAGI PRES] I know it's
rude but I can't help laughing!
[SATO] Yarizui!
[SATO] Go!
Now!
[YARIZUI] Sato, behind you!
[BOTH] The moment
we've been waiting for!
[SHAGA] The Ice Witch.
She's down.
[SATO] Yarizui.
I can't believe it.
[SAWAGI PRES] It was well worth
the long wait, wasn't it, Kyo?
[SAWAGI VP] Yes,
it was, Sis. It really was.
You must be
so angry with us.
I know I'd be furious
if I was in your place.
Oh, please tell me
you want revenge,
'cause we really
wanna fight you again!
You come find us as soon
as you're ready, okay?
We'll wait patiently
for you until then.
It's all mine.
Good work, Sis.
Now let's get out of here.
How could this happen?
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
Don't forget,
our name is Orthros.
We don't run and we do not hide.
[SAWAGI VP] Come and find us.
Hunt us to the
ends of the earth.
[SAWAGI PRES] If you dare.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Maybe we should've been more
careful with our
wording back there.
I mean, what if the
Pervert decides to stalk us?
They do call him
the Pervert for a reason!
[SAWAGI VP] Yeah,
you say that now,
but you'd complain even more
if he didn't start stalking us.
Well yeah,
I'd be insulted!