[alarm ringing]
[ASEBI] Just five more minutes.
Nooooooo!!!
[crash]
[ASEBI]
Wow.
[ASEBI] Looks like
another beautiful day!
[SHAGA] You want
to make a bento for Sato?
Are you serious?
[ASEBI] Uh-huh!
I mean he ate a
whole bunch of those
cookies I made the other day,
so I figure he must like
my cooking an awful lot!
So that means
he'd probably be super
happy if I made him
a full-fledged bento!
Oh. Yeah, I guess
that makes sense.
I'm gonna make it
extra big in case he's hungry!
That's great!
Uh, good idea!
Yeah.
I'm sure he'll love it!
Well, I hope so!
Anyway, bye!
I gotta get cooking pretty soon!
[SHAGA] All right,
give it your best shot!
[ASEBI] I sure will!
[SHAGA] Poor Sato.
He's so dead.
What is Shiraume
doing at my school?
[car tires screaching
and collision]
What'd I do... this time?
[VIDEO GAME VOICE] Fight One.
Ready.
Go!
[OSHIROI] So, Sato, what
happened to your cheek?
[SATO] Well, how
should I put this?
Let's just say a wild
animal attacked me.
[OSHIROI] Hold on,
are you telling me you
were ra--ra--ra--ra--
Not even close.
You need to calm down.
[YARIZUI] Here.
This ought to help.
Hey. Thanks, Yarizui,
I really appreciate it.
Do you think
it would be best to
skip out on tonight's brawl?
No way!
I'm not missing it!
[ASEBI] Wait!
Shaga?
Uh, hey.
[SATO] Hi, Asebi.
I'll lend you my good
luck charm just this once.
You're gonna thank me later.
Hope you're hungry.
I made a special
bento just for you!
Huh?
For me?
[SATO THINKS] Jeez, Shaga.
Don't scare me like that.
I was afraid she
was gonna pull out
something weird,
but this looks awesome.
Well, here I go!
Okay! Dig in!
[SATO THINKS] First,
let's try the pork filet.
[SATO THINKS] Wha--
what the hell is this?
Looking at it,
it has to be a pork filet,
but the flavor is--It
tastes like banana?
That's not right.
This tastes like raw tuna!
It's sweet!
Like it was covered in sugar, or
honey, or soda or something!
[SATO THINKS] Whoa!
It's spicy!
But why?
And do I dare try this one?
[SATO THINKING] It doesn't
taste like anything!
But--but at least the
rice won't betray me!
[SATO THINKS] Coriander?
But it's rice!
[SATO THINKS] I don't even know
what I'm eating anymore.
It's over.
It's all over.
My taste buds are
completely wrecked.
So?
Is it good?
Yeah.
It's great.
Okay. Better eat
every last bite!
Uh. Sure.
You bet I will!
Wow. Your sweat
is so beautiful!
Keep it up, Sato!
[SARAH] Even good guys blow it!
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[ASEBI] I sure will!
[SHIRAUME THINKS]
That's--no, never mind.
I'll just have
to ignore her for now.
[car tires screaching
and collision]
[SHIRAUME THINKS] After all,
I have a battle to attend to.
[SATO] I got here on time!
You have no idea
what I've been through!
[SATO] You gotta find
me something to wear!
Please!
It's an emergency!
[SATO] Those bullets are real!
[SECURITY 9A] Fire in the hole!
[SECURITY GUARD] Takeshima!
Over there!
This boy is from your school.
Am I correct? His name
is Yo Sato, I believe.
Yes.
That's correct.
[SAWAGI PRES] Excellent.
Now that you've
confirmed his identity
and seen the
footage we captured,
will you also confirm that
this is an act of trespassing,
along with what can
only be described
as public indecency and
disturbing the peace?
[SHIRAUME] Indeed.
It's just as you say.
Very well then...
On behalf of Marutomi High
School, in response to the
strange and perverse
display we've seen just now,
we demand a written
apology from your school.
[SAWAGI VP]
Despite these conditions.
I do believe that it
would be best to resolve
this matter privately to
avoid creating a scandal.
[SHIRAUME]
I couldn't agree more.
I was going to
suggest the same thing.
[SHIRAUME] This girl is
from your school, yes?
I believe her name
is Ayame Shaga.
We have determined,
that in addition to the lewd
acts depicted here, she has
trespassed on school property
on numerous occasions
without authorization.
To facilitate these actions,
she also acquired one of
our school's uniforms,
and has been
brazenly attempting to
blend in with the rest
of the students.
How unfortunate.
[SAWAGI PRES]
Let's put this behind us.
I suggest we reach
an agreement that will
preserve the relationship
between our two schools.
We are equals, after all.
Yes.
I think that's a
splendid proposal.
But there's one thing to settle.
[SHIRAUME] On behalf
of Karasuda High
I demand a written
apology from your school.
And that's final.
I will continue
this conversation
once you agree
to that condition.
[both laugh]
[SAWAGI PRES]
It's not fair, Kyo!
I don't wanna apologize to her!
She's so mean!
I warned you that
this might happen
if you rubbed it in
too much, didn't I?
The written apology
document was to be used
as a last resort,
not something to flaunt around.
I know!
But you saw her--she
was so full of herself!
I wanted to wipe
that smug look off her face!
Kyo!
C'mon.
Look on the bright side,
it's not as if we lost anything,
it was just a tie.
Besides, the information
we learned about
those Wolves is worth
more than any apology.
[SHIRAUME] Thanks to you.
I was humiliated today.
[Sato cries out]
[GIRL STUDENT 9B] Oh.
Miss President.
Welcome back.
[GIRL STUDENT 9A] I filled out
the papers for the next meeting,
so they just need your approval.
[SHIRAUME] How considerate.
I'll get to that.
[girls scream]
[GIRL STUDENT 9B] What's that?
[GIRL STUDENT 9A] Gross!
[water splash]
[SHIRAUME] Today
certainly was tiring.
I need to relax.
I should call Oshiroi.
[OSHIROI]
"What's wrong, Saito?"
"You're glistening with sweat!
Finally feeling the
heat, are you?"
[OSHIROI]
"What have you done?
My body's on fire!"
[OSHIROI] Saito tries to resist.
[OSHIROI] But his willpower--
is rapidly fading,
as he is overwhelmed with
the lust of a salacious beast!
[OSHIROI] Will he give in?
Find out next time!
[OSHIROI]
I really outdid myself!
[OSHIROI] Oh wow, I got a whole
lot of hits on the site today!
Let me see.
I'm looking at well over ten
thousand views for this week.
I must have some new readers!
[notification sound]
It's Ume.
Hello Oshiroi, how are you?
[OSHIROI] Fine, but--
[SHIRAUME]
Did I call at a bad time?
[OSHIROI] No, not really.
I was just a little startled,
since you're calling a bit
earlier than you usually do.
I'm sorry. I was suddenly
struck with the
need to see your face
and I just couldn't resist.
Speaking of which,
your cheeks are a bit red.
Oh, really?
[SHIRAUME] You don't happen
to have a fever, do you?
No, it's not that.
[SHIRAUME] Perhaps,
you would like me to
stop by and check on you?
Oh no,
I think I'll be fine!
There's no need for that!
[Oshiroi cries out]
[SHIRAUME] Are you okay?
What's wrong, Oshiroi?
Ow, my head!
No! Saito!
Please don't die on me, Saito!
Gone. It's all gone.
[OSHIROI] I'm sorry, Saito.
Rest in peace.
[SHIRAUME] Oshiroi?
Did something happen?
Hello?
[SATO] Ben-To.
Ume?
[SHIRAUME] You
shouldn't exert yourself.
It's all right now.
I promise that I'll take
very good care of you.
There's nothing to
worry about anymore.
Just relax.
[OSHIROI] Well,
I wasn't really worried
about anything to begin with.
Also, when did you get here?
[SHIRAUME] I came as
soon as I saw you pass out.
[OSHIROI]
"Pass out"?
Perhaps your
memory is fuzzy,
but you let out a scream
when we were chatting earlier.
While the camera seemed
to be malfunctioning,
it appeared that you had
collapsed on your bed.
I didn't collapse so
much as I just went to sleep.
Poor thing.
You really frightened
me, you know.
So, I quickly changed your
clothes, and tucked you in.
[OSHIROI] You what?
I took your clothes off.
[SHIRAUME] And of course.
Your underwear.
[SHIRAUME] Oh no, this won't do.
Look, your cheeks
are burning up.
[OSHIROI] Yeah, but I mean,
uh-- it's not a fever.
[SHIRAUME] I'm here for you,
it's okay to admit
that you're sick.
No, you've got
it all wrong.
I'm telling you,
I don't have a fever.
[OSHIROI] If you don't believe
me, use a thermometer.
Why would I lie?
Yes, of course.
I did already.
But this one is broken.
It said your temperature
was normal.
[SHIRAUME]
There lie down and rest a bit.
[OSHIROI] Uh, sure.
Don't be afraid.
I'll be right here by your side.
'Kay.
[stomach growl]
Oh my. You want
a late night snack?
Oh, uh--I--
I guess so.
I had a feeling
that this might happen,
so I prepared some food for you.
Oh.
Wow!
A rice porridge bento!
I went home and
made it when your fever
started to pass so I
assure you, it's quite fresh.
That's nice,
but my fever passed
because I never had
one in the first place.
[SHIRAUME]
I kept it in a thermos,
so it's the perfect temperature.
Eat it all while
it's still warm.
All of it?
Are you sure?
Of course.
I made it just for you,
so you don't have
to worry about sharing.
Did I get it right?
[OSHIROI] Yep!
A little salty,
just how I like it.
I'm glad. There's a
bit on your face.
Eat every last bite,
and I'm sure
you'll feel better in no time.
I guess so, but I
was fine to begin with.
[SHIRAUME] Let's see.
Would you like some
fried salmon too?
Oh.
Yes, please.
Here.
You were so hot,
we should wipe all
that sweat off your
body when you're done.
[OSHIROI] Huh?
Ume?
I think I'm gonna be fine.
I didn't sweat more than usual.
[SHIRAUME] You don't
have to act so brave.
If you neglect to clean
yourself at a time like this,
you could end up with a rash
or something even worse.
[OSHIROI] Yeah, but--
It's all right. Now turn
around and face me.
I'd rather not.
I'm doing this
for your own good.
[OSHIROI] I know, but--This
is really embarrassing!
We've taken baths
together countless times.
Why are you so shy now?
'Cause, well,
that's not the same.
I completely understand.
What?
When we took a bath
we were both naked,
so I need to strip as well.
[OSHIROI] Ume.
Please don't.
I don't like it.
No more!
[SHIRAUME] Hey, Oshiroi.
[OSHIROI] Can we just stop?
[SHIRAUME] Did
something just fall?
Why are
you so scared?
[SHIRAUME] What
kind of book is this?
[OSHIROI] Oh, it's a-- just--
[OSHIROI] What in
the hell was that?
Hey, Sato. You have
got to check this out!
Come on.
I promise, this is
right up your alley.
[UCHIMOTO] Go ahead.
Borrow it for a while.
I've already had
my fun, trust me.
What's wrong?
It's fine! I know
you're into this stuff!
[UCHIMOTO] Martial Arts
Mastery, Volume One.
Pervert Repulsion Techniques!
The lady in this video
kicks the crap out
of every guy that
comes close to her.
Plus, when she's
done, she even steps on
them with her high heels!
And it's in beautiful HD!
[SATO] Yeah, not interested.
[UCHIMOTO] I thought
we were bros!
Don't you like this?
[SATO] Look,
I told you, I'm not--
You have some very
interesting hobbies, don't you?
No, that's not--Hey.
What was a
perverse magazine
like this doing
in Oshiroi's room?
I don't know!
And I don't really care, either!
[SHIRAUME]
Don't play dumb with me.
[SHIRAUME] Would you stop
harassing poor Oshiroi?
You should be ashamed
of yourself, making this smut.
You seriously
think I put that together?
[SHIRAUME] Then who did?
Why else would
Oshiroi have this book?
She likes muscles!
She's writing a novel!
You haven't read it, have you?
It's full of muscle men!
And one of
the characters in this
messed up story of
hers is based on me!
I guess she put
my face on those dudes
to make her weird fantasy
just a little more real--
[SHIRAUME] For you information,
I read Oshiroi's writings
every time she updates her page.
And I assure you, they have none
of the smut you mentioned.
I'm also certain
that Oshiroi would never
make a tasteless
collage like this.
Not in a million years.
And if you think she
based a character off of you,
you are simply delusional.
[GIRL STUDENT 9C]
Hey, what's this?
Now you've made
me angry.
[punching and Sato cries out]
[UCHIMOTO] So hot.
[GIRL STUDENT 9C]
Oh my gosh, he is so gross.
[GIRL STUDENT 9D]
What a pervert.
He's such a pathetic loser.
[GIRL STUDENT 9C] Somebody
should neuter this freak.
[GIRL STUDENT 9D]
"Freak"?
He's more like a worm.
You scored, Sato!
Verbal abuse, too!
[SATO THINKS] On the upside.
[GIRL STUDENT 9C] So disgusting.
[GIRL STUDENT 9D] Just die!
[SATO] At least
the view is nice.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[YARIZUI] They say when you
sneeze, someone is talking
about you, but what
about three sneezes?
Someone fell for you.
Is that it?
[YARIZUI]
Well, it's silly anyway.
[sneeze]
[YARIZUI] Wait, four?
What does four sneezes mean?
Hm.
Don't miss the next episode!
Who, knows what
might happen when--
Actually,
I have no idea what's
going to happen,
nobody told me! Help!
Next time.
Why don't we take a pass on
doing the episode
preview, 'kay, Sis?