You must
be so angry with us.
I know I'd be furious if
I was in your place.
[SAWAGI PRES]
I hope you want revenge,
'cause we really
wanna fight you again!
You come find us as
soon as you're ready, okay?
[SAWAGI VP] Come and find us.
Hunt us to the
ends of the earth.
[SAWAGI PRES] If you dare.
[NIKAIDO] Hang on.
I wanna ask--you something.
Forget Orthros.
Who are you, really?
Well, my name
is Kyo Sawagi,
and this is my sister
who shares the same name.
It may sound odd but
they're written as two
different characters--
Why do you always have
to take things so literally?
It was a hypothetical question,
he didn't ask for our names.
Oh. Sorry.
Where in the hell did
the two of you come from?
[SAWAGI PRES] Nice try buddy
but there's no way I'm giving
our home address to some
skeevy dude we just met.
[SAWAGI PRES] However,
since we told you to hunt us,
I suppose it's only fair
that we let you know
which supermarkets
we're planning to hit next.
Well?
What's it gonna be?
Do you want to know or don'tcha?
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SAWAGI PRES] Kyo!
Oh, yes!
I'm in heaven!
It feels so good!
Would you please
cut it out, Sis?
I know you're excited
about our victory,
but what are the
neighbors going to think?
[SAWAGI PRES] How
you can be so calm?
We witnessed the
power of the Ice Witch!
And, not only did we
totally overpower her,
but we also snatched her bento.
It just feels so good!
Yeah.
It was pretty awesome.
This is what we've always
dreamed about, Kyo.
Remember?
Ever since you and
I were little kids we've
known that we were
destined to be Wolves.
Now, our dream has
finally become a reality.
[YOUNG SAWAGI PRES] Found you!
[SAWAGI PRES]
Back then, we had no idea
those brawlers
were called Wolves.
I wonder when
we figured that out.
[SAWAGI VP] It had to
be before we started school.
[SAWAGI VP] When our
kindergarten teacher asked us
what we wanted to be when
we grew up, we answered:
[BOTH] When we're
all grown up we wanna be Wolves!
Yeah. We'd already
made up our minds.
Uh-huh.
We knew from the start,
we wanted to be noble Wolves.
Noble.
[SAWAGI PRES CRIES]
Whoa, where did
all this come from?
There was nothing noble
about what I did last night!
I'm sorry,
but I couldn't help myself;
I said something really
mean to the Pervert!
What did you say to him?
"Hey Perv, it doesn't
look like there's an
ounce of muscle on that
wimpy body of yours!
Next time you're gonna be a
big, red puddle on the floor!"
I probably shouldn't say that to
someone while I'm
strangling them.
Hey Kyo, are you sure that
wasn't just a bad dream?
Oh. Now that you mention it,
I guess it was.
But still, what if he decides he
doesn't want to fight
us anymore?
If that happens, what're
we gonna do, Kyo?
I don't think we have
any reason to worry.
If it'll make you feel better,
you could always
go up to him and--
Oh, I know!
The next time I see him I'll
walk right up and apologize.
I mean, he has to forgive me if
I give him a heartfelt
apology, right?
[GIRL STUDENT 11A] Thank
goodness we finally ditched her.
[GIRL STUDENT 11B]
Spoke too soon.
[GIRL STUDENT 11C] Wait for me!
[GIRL STUDENT 11B]
Hey, we thought we'd lost you.
[GIRL STUDENT 11C]
Yeah, I turned around
and you guys were gone.
[OSHIROI] Yo!
Are you ready?
Time to start a new day!
So tell me,
how did things go
at the Ho-ki Mart yesterday?
You get yourself a bento?
No, I didn't.
I got my butt kicked hardcore,
and Yarizui did, too.
[OSHIROI] That's too bad 'cause
I did awesome on my novel!
The two-person team
thing really inspired me.
I'm tellin' ya, it practically
wrote itself, y'know?
Orthros are strong,
but I never would've
thought they were strong
enough to beat Yarizui.
I had to start writing
the old fashioned way
with paper and pen because
my laptop exploded but it
makes me feel
more like a real writer;
I've got hand cramps
and everything!
In fact,
it's cramping right now.
[SATO] Yknow,
I feel like this is all
my fault somehow,
but what could I do?
I mean, it's not like I could
stop them by myself.
I can't believe it, she was
kidnapped right in front of us!
[SATO] I've gotta
apologize to Yarizui.
[SATO] She's not in class.
[BRUNETTE] Well,
well, if it isn't the Pup.
[BRUNETTE] Lemme guess,
you're looking for the
Ice Witch, aren't you?
Uh. Yeah.
[BRUNETTE] I was
worried, too, so I came to
check on her but
she's absent today.
Huh? Do you
know why?
[BRUNETTE] Maybe
she's gone into hiding?
After all, that was
a harsh way to lose.
To be honest,
I've been toying with
the idea of skipping
tonight's brawl myself.
It's not as much fun when the
odds are stacked against you.
No, you can't
give up now!
Who cares about the odds,
you're still stacked!
[BRUNETTE] You
really are a pervert.
[GIRL STUDENT 11F] Wait.
You wanna know
about the Sawagi sisters?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
I just figured since they went
to middle school with all of
you lovely ladies,
you probably know
them better than anybody else.
[GIRL STUDENT 11G]
We don't really know
all that much about them.
I mean, we didn't hang out
with them or anything, sorry.
[SHAGA] But there's
gotta be something--
[GIRL STUDENT 11H]
Hey, check it out!
[GIRL STUDENT 11G]
I can't believe he
texted you that picture!
Geez.
Thanks a lot for
nothin', hoe-bags.
Hey Nikaido.
I thought I told
you not to hound me.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm out asking
about them right now.
[ASEBI] Look what I found!
Isn't it cute?
[SHAGA] Um, Asebi.
I've made friends
with Mr. Butterfly!
[ASEBI] That tickles!
Uh. Just don't
worry, okay?
I'm gonna keep asking around
until I can get some info.
[ASEBI] Seriously!
That tickles!
[SATO] Two-oh-one.
This must be it.
[YARIZUI] Who is it?
Uh. Hey,
it's me, Yarizui.
[YARIZUI] Sato?
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
I hope I didn't catch
you at a bad time,
but I was worried about you.
So I came by.
[SATO THINKS] She's not dressed.
[YARIZUI] Why are you
staring at me like that?
Oh, uh-- I'm sorry.
I don't look
that bad, do I?
Because you're getting
me all worried now.
Oh, no. Uh. You
look just fine to me.
I dropped in outta the blue so
if this isn't a good time--
[YARIZUI] Come in.
Wait, but are you sure?
[YARIZUI] Of course, I'm sure.
I already had a slight cold
but it got worse overnight.
I woke up feeling
absolutely horrible.
I've been lying
in bed all day long.
Huh?
[YARIZUI] Yeah,
I'm sorry I forgot call you.
I didn't mean to make you worry.
[SATO THINKS] Oh, I get it now.
Everything okay?
Uh, yeah, sorry!
I thought you might be sick,
so I brought these for you.
That's so sweet.
Thank you.
[SATO] It's covered
in her sweat!
It was on her forehead until
just a few seconds ago!
Hey Sato?
Do you mind checking to see
if my fever's gone down?
No prob.
I'm afraid you're
still warm, Yarizui.
I'm sorry, but would you
please stay with me tonight?
Don't apologize.
I'd be happy to stay with you
and share some coffee.
[YARIZUI] Do you mind
if I have a bottle of Pocari?
[SATO] Not at all!
Go right ahead!
The cold feels
good on my skin.
Oh!
I guess you've still got
a bit of a fever, huh?
Yeah, guess so,
but I'm sure it'll
go down eventually.
Look, I'm sorry
about yesterday.
[SATO] It was all my fault.
I never should've
let my guard down.
No, it wasn't
your fault.
I simply wasn't strong
enough to take them on.
Next time,
we're gonna win for sure.
Yarizui.
Yeah, I agree. Once you
start feeling better,
we can give it
another shot, okay?
[YARIZUI]
The day after tomorrow.
We have to.
Summer will be over
soon, and that means--
That means
that this might be
our last chance
to get an eel bento!
Yeah, exactly.
[YARIZUI] The Super Audrey
has an eel special
every year and
it's absolutely amazing.
[YARIZUI] Delicious freshwater
eel grilled over charcoals.
They cook a new
batch each hour and the
customers only
purchase the fresh ones.
Now listen.
That night, when the
God of Discounts gets to work,
all of the eel bento
boxes are marked
half-price regardless of
when they were made.
You're tellin' me we can
get fresh eel for half-price?
[YARIZUI] I've got to
get my hands on one.
So do me a favor, if you happen
to run into the twins tonight,
will you tell them to meet
me at Super Audrey?
The eel bento
is gonna be all mine!
[BRUNETTE] Ben-To.
[GIRL STUDENT 11F]
Hey, whatever happened with
that guy who texted you?
[GIRL STUDENT 11H]
Oh, I blew him off.
He turned out to
be a total creep.
[SPORTS TEAM GUY 11A]
Karasuda High!
Fight! Fight!
[WALLA: SPORTS TEAM] On! On!
[SPORTS TEAM GUY 11A]
Karasuda High!
Fight! Fight!
[WALLA: SPORTS TEAM] On! On!
[SATO] Orthros asked
you to invite me?
[NIKAIDO] More like
they forced me to.
[SATO] But what could they
possibly want with me?
[SAWAGI PRES] Uh, Pervert?
I'm--
[SAWAGI PRES] I'm--
[SATO] I get the
feeling she's trying to say,
"I'm gonna strangle you, Perv!"
I'm--
I'm sorry about all
the terrible things
I said the other day.
Please, forgive me!
Thank you, but you
didn't say anything that bad.
Do you mind if
we take a timeout?
Sure, go right ahead.
[SAWAGI VP] I told you
that was just a dream.
Now what are we gonna do?
[SAWAGI PRES] I know, I
should've listened to you, Sis.
[SATO] Those two have
some serious issues.
[NIKAIDO] No joke. Tell
me something I don't know.
[BENTO BRAWLER 11B] Check it out
guys, Orthros are here again.
Well, I guess there's no
reason to stick around.
They're scared of us, Kyo!
Look at them
trying to sneak out!
Please excuse my sister's
rude behavior; she can be
extremely competitive.
What's so rude about it?
I simply think that losers
need to know their place.
I mean, look at the two of you;
you're like--You're like--
They're like a couple
of dumb dogs, right?
Yeah!
Way to go!
You guys are just two dumb dogs
who aren't even
worthy of our time!
And you're gonna
be begging us for mercy
when we wipe this filthy
floor with your faces!
"Filthy?" Don't you think
that's kind of insulting
to the people
who work here, Sis?
Uh. You're gonna
beg for mercy when
we wipe this clean
and shiny floor wi--
That's too much;
now it sounds like
you're mocking them.
We're done playing
your little games, ladies.
We're gonna
beat you tonight.
Oh, you think so?
Well, good luck but
we're not gonna be
defeated by a couple
of dumb dogs.
[SHAGA] I see.
So they beat the crap
outta you guys again, huh?
You are two dumb dogs.
Thanks, Shaga.
Enough about us, okay?
Did you get the info
I asked you for or not?
[SHAGA] Didn't your mother
teach you any manners?
Girls don't like pushy guys.
[NIKAIDO]
Just answer me, would ya?
[SHAGA] Okay, okay.
I'll give you your
info but only because
I'm a kind,
generous person, jerk.
[SHAGA] Have you ever
heard of the Sonic Store?
No, doesn't ring a bell.
[SHAGA] It first sprung
up not too far from here,
in Yumehiro, but it was so
popular that it became a chain.
But get this,
the company that operates
it is the Sawagi Corporation.
[SATO] Wait a second.
Are you trying to
say that Orthros--
[SHAGA] Yep, they're the
daughters of the owner.
They used to live in Yumehiro,
and they moved here
about three years ago.
That's interesting.
Happen to know if they were
Wolves before they moved away?
From what I've heard,
they were active Wolves
in Yumehiro, but they stopped
brawling when they came here.
It sounds like they ran into
some trouble back home.
[NIKAIDO] I'll see ya later.
I'm gonna go to
Yumehiro to investigate.
Okay, drive safely!
So, do you wanna
play some Virtua?
Alright,
but while I'm here
I really gotta find Orthros.
Yarizui said to tell them
about the eel bento--
Oh yeah!
Super Audrey's eel bento
special is coming up!
I'm looking forward to it, too.
[SATO] I was supposed to
tell them to show up there,
but I'm gonna have
to leave the job to you!
[SHAGA] Huh? Why
do I have to do it?
Tell 'em Yarizui will
be waiting for them there.
See ya!
Wait!
Hold on, Sato!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Oh man, this sucks.
[SHAGA] Come to the Super Audrey
tomorrow night for
half-price eel bento.
The Ice Witch wants you to
know she'll be waiting for you.
Oh, we wouldn't
miss it for the world.
Please tell her
thanks for extending
such a generous invitation.
[SAWAGI PRES] I assume
you'll be there, too.
See you tomorrow.
[SAWAGI PRES]
I'm so excited, Kyo!
Aren't you?
We get a chance to brawl
against the Ice Witch again!
[SAWAGI VP] Yes.
It's all very exciting.
I know.
[SAWAGI VP] Oh no,
it's a Dog Day.
Just like three years ago.
Yeah, I almost forgot.
It was a Dog Day.
This can't be good.
[SATO] What do you
mean you've gotten worse?
How in the heck did that happen?
[YARIZUI] I told you
not to visit me today.
Well, too bad!
Now tell me how you've
gotten even sicker!
[YARIZUI] All right, fine.
I thought it would
be a good idea
to prepare myself for battle.
Okay.
[YARIZUI] So last night,
I decided to take a really
hot bath thinking that
it would kill the virus.
Okay.
[YARIZUI] When I got out,
my skin was burning up,
so I put on my PJs and
sat in front of the AC.
Okay.
[YARIZUI] And it felt
so good I fell asleep.
[SATO] I wanna be mad,
but that sounds like
something I would do.
[SATO] Maybe you should
forget about the Super Audrey--
No way! I can't let
a cold get me down!
[SATO] But you can't fight
anyone in your current state.
Are you
giving up on me?
I'll show you.
I want you to go to
the pharmacy for me.
I just need some cold
medicine and I'll be fine.
[SATO] Are you sure about that?
The bento brawl
is tomorrow night.
I know!
I'll be fine, Sato!
[YARIZUI] Please.
Do this for me.
[SATO THINKS]
She sounds terrible...
I've gotta do whatever
I can to help her out.
[FEMALE CLERK 11A]
Good evening, sir!
[NIKAIDO] Have you
ever heard of Orthros?
Sorry, but I don't
believe I've had the
pleasure of meeting
you before, Wolf.
Now who told you to
come here and talk to me?
A lovely lady
who was once
known as The Monarch Butterfly.
Matsuba.
Please give her my
best regards, will you?
Of course I will, that is,
if you tell me what
happened three years ago.
I've already tried asking
some of the other Wolves
but they just ignore me
and refuse to answer.
I called her out of desperation
and she said you'd
be able to help me.
[GLASSES MAN 11A] I'm afraid
I can't tell you anything.
As you know, every town
has its own set of rules.
The last thing I want
to do is break them,
'cause I'd have to
give up being a Wolf.
Although, I suppose
there wouldn't be any
harm in helping someone who
knows one of my old friends.
[GLASSES MAN 11A]
All right fine,
I'll tell you because I'm
feeling charitable today.
[GLASSES MAN 11A]
Back then, there was a
pair of Wolves who took
on an odd name.
That of a two-headed dog from
ancient Greek Mythology.
However, they were
soon driven out of town.
By a Wolf called
Heracles' Combo.
Wait, seriously?
But why?
[COMBO MAN 11A]
Look how scared they are!
[COMBO GIRL 11A]
That's what you get, brats!
[COMBO MAN 11B]
You're not so tough now.
[COMBO MAN 11A]
You girls are goin' down!
[SAWAGI PRES] Why?
Why are you doing this?
Stop it!
Go away!
What did we ever do to you?
[SAWAGI VP] Kyo!
Kyo, wake up!
[SAWAGI VP] You okay?
It sounds like you had a bad
dream about that day again, huh?
[SAWAGI VP] This is
getting out of hand, Sis.
Maybe we should call it off.
No way.
We've gotta fight.
We can't let the Ice Witch and
those dumb dogs win that easily.
[SAWAGI PRES] It's not going
to be like last time, okay?
I promise.
[GLASSES MAN 11A] It didn't
take long for news of Orthros'
return to reach us
here in Yumehiro.
My first thought was,
"There's a Dog Day
coming up, this is just
like three years ago."
I have no doubt.
Heracles' Combo will show up.
You've got to find a way
to save them somehow.
[HERACLES] It's time to drive
you away again, Orthros.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[PHARMACIST LADY 11A]
In that case,
this suppository
should do the trick.
But you have to be careful;
some people don't like
taking suppositories.
[SATO THINKS] I can't blame 'em.
Who wants to stick
medicine up their butt?
I don't know how
Yarizui feels about them,
but she did say she wanted
something fast acting.
[PHARMACIST LADY 11A] A
lot of people find it difficult
to put it in by
themselves the first time.
They need someone
to do it for them.
[SATO THINKS] Wait, I'll have
to put it up her butt?
No way!
Forget it!
I can't do that!
[SATO] If you'll excuse me.
Hey, Oshiroi?
I need help.
[SHIRAUME]
What do you want, Sato?
Shiraume?
[SHIRAUME] That's right.
Oshiroi's in the bathroom.
I don't think you should
be answering her phone.
[SHIRAUME] Do you have
something you need to ask her?
If not, I'm hanging up.
No! I can't
do this by myself!
I mean-- I need her to help
me put in a suppository.
[SHIRAUME] You want her
to stick it up your butt?
No, that's not
what I meant!
You don't understand,
I need her to do it for Yarizui!
[SHIRAUME] If she didn't want to
do it, then why would Oshiroi?
You've really pissed
me off tonight.
You'd better watch
your back tomorrow.
You know sir,
these gel caps are
pretty fast-acting, too.
Would you like
to try them instead?
[SATO] Yes.
[PHARMACIST LADY 11A]
Thanks for visiting us.
I hope your friend feels better.
Heracles shows up again
but what's the
secret of his combo?
Which brawler will take home the
coveted half-price eel bento?
And will the medicine
that I suggested work?
Next time:
Ben-To episode twelve.
It's the last one, so please
read the instructions carefully.