[OSHIROI] The battle with the
diabolical Anarch had begun.
[OSHIROI] "I'm gonna
ruffle your feathers
from top to bottom,
little chicky."
[OSHIROI] And so he did,
tearing at the innocent Saito
from behind and giving him
a very dirty surprise!
But the Anarch was
also using the power
of his minions,
the Shabrael Rachet,
to take over all the
steaming hot saunas in town.
Legs sprawled in
defeat, bodies glistening,
the boys submit to the
Anarch, longing for release.
But Saito attempted
to penetrate the Anarch's
defenses with
his rock hard passion.
Will our hero end
up on top or on bottom?
Muscle Cop Episode 6!
[OSHIROI]
Don't you dare miss it!
[MATSUBA]
What a lovely surprise.
Did my old rival come
here to cheer me up?
[KANESHIRO] Sorry,
but I'm not one
to bother over
things like that.
I actually came
here to say goodbye.
I'm afraid I have to
leave the city for a while.
[MATSUBA] You're leaving?
[KANESHIRO] Yeah, it turns
out I'll be studying abroad.
I see.
Good for you.
It's nice to know that
you're as free as ever.
I'm jealous.
But to be perfectly
honest, I was hoping
you'd be able to put
a stop to Endo's plan.
[KANESHIRO] I wouldn't
worry about that.
Wolves have their own
set of rules, you know.
Those who break them will be
thrown out of the
pack eventually.
[MATSUBA] You think?
I still believe in the
pride the Wolves possess.
I know you do.
[KANESHIRO] Well, take
care, Monarch Butterfly.
[opening theme]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[YARIZUI] It seems
everyone is here.
So let's begin, shall we?
[YARIZUI] Do you hear me,
Wolves of the West?
[WEST WOLF 6A]
Get over yourself.
What, you think
you're our leader?
[WEST WOLF 6B]
That's fine by me.
It's the Ice Witch
we're talking about here.
[WEST WOLF 6C] Just hurry
and get this started already.
[YARIZUI] I believe I've
already told you everything I
know about the Monarch's plot,
so I don't need to go
over the details, right?
[WEST WOLF 6A] He's planning
on taking over the West, right?
Monarch sure is
thinking big these days.
[WEST WOLF 6B]
He's just an idiot.
[WEST WOLF 6C]
Even if he comes out
swinging with all of his men,
what does he think
he's gonna accomplish?
[WEST WOLF 6B] Hey, stop it!
Why the hell're
you peeing in public?
[WEST WOLF 6C]
That's not me, man.
Chill out.
It's just a dog
marking his territory.
[WEST WOLF 6B] Look at this guy!
He can't hold it in, either!
And to top it
all off, he's naked!
[WEST WOLF 6D] Ew.
Gross.
[WEST WOLF 6A] Anyway, the
Monarch can come if he likes,
but there's no way he's
beating us in our own territory.
[WEST WOLF 6B] Exactly.
That's what I'm talkin' about!
We know how good the
bentos from our turf taste.
As long as we have
that hunger we won't let
anyone take them away from us!
[YARIZUI] I see.
Your hunger will be
satisfied that easily?
[WEST WOLF 6A]
What are you implying?
So long as the Monarch's
able to wreak havoc,
there's a hole in my
stomach that'll never be filled.
[WEST WOLF 6D]
So you have a plan?
I think it's time for
us to go on the offensive.
While you're all fighting,
I'm going after his home
base-- Ralph Store.
[SATO] What?
And you're positive
this is the only way?
All right, but what do you
want us to do to help out?
[YARIZUI] Oh, it's quite simple.
You'll take care
of our home base.
Yeah, that sounds like
a lot of responsibility to me.
[WEST WOLF 6B] They
sure won't be expecting that.
[WEST WOLF 6A] You do
whatever you want, Ice Witch.
We'll keep fighting,
eating and protecting
our pride, just like always.
[YARIZUI] I'm counting on you.
Uh, okay.
[YARIZUI] You know what to do.
Let's make our
preparations for the battle.
Don't you dare let the
West fall while I'm gone.
[YARIZUI] All right.
Be careful out there.
[SATO] Uh, Yarizui, are you
sure you're okay alone?
[YARIZUI]
At Ralph Store,
the bento with a seal is
zangee chicken karaage.
It's made just
for Wolves like us.
Created by Macchan,
a former Wolf herself.
From what I'm told,
its flavor is unrivaled.
All right, but that isn't
really the issue here.
There's no need
to act so worried.
I'm just going to
grab some dinner,
just like any other night.
[OSHIROI] She's so cool.
[YARIZUI THINKS]
It's over tonight, Monarch.
I'm putting an end to this.
[SHAGA]
"Monarch Butterfly?" Who's that?
[EAST WOLF 6A] That's what
they used to call Macchan back
when she was active as a Wolf.
She was strong,
maybe the strongest.
And more beautiful than
you could ever imagine.
All of the East Wolves
looked up to her;
she was like a hero
or a goddess to us.
Oh, thank you.
Anyway, about a year ago,
the Monarch Butterfly had
a battle with the Wizard,
who was considered the strongest
Wolf in the West at the time.
[EAST WOLF 6A] Both were
evenly matched, but when their
epic struggle reached
its conclusion.
[EAST WOLF 6A]
It was the Wizard,
who ultimately claimed
the laurel wreath seal.
[EAST WOLF 6A] But that night,
the Wizard was
found unconscious,
passed out in the
middle of the road.
And next to him, there was an
empty bento on the ground.
Huh? So what
happened to him?
The Wizard may
have prevailed in battle,
but it left him so exhausted,
he didn't have the
strength to return home.
[EAST WOLF 6A] But even though
his body refused to go on,
he wouldn't let
the food go to waste.
He savored every last bite
until his consciousness faded.
I never thought
of the Wizard like that.
Though to be honest,
I can't really think of anyone
who'd be crazy enough to
collapse in the middle of street
and keep eating until
they passed out.
[EAST WOLF 6A] If you'd seen the
fight, maybe you'd understand...
By the way,
Tadaaki Endo was
an underclassmen
who attended the same
school that Macchan went to.
As you know,
he's the current "Monarch."
[EAST WOLF 6A] After Macchan got
married and quit being a Wolf,
he and his gang
stepped up and brought
the East together in a snap.
[EAST WOLF 6A] But he
still can't cope with the fact
that his old upperclassman
lost that battle.
And that's why he
wants to take over
the West while the
Wizard is still here.
[EAST WOLF 6A] Not quite.
The truth is,
his big plan to conquer
both sides is
nothing but a bluff.
The only thing he's
really interested in
is the title of
"the strongest Wolf."
He didn't like the way that
battle ended a year ago.
So he's trying to recreate it
and make sure his side wins.
If he's supposed to be the
successor to the
Monarch Butterfly,
there's no better
way to prove that
than to defeat the
Wizard's successor.
Hold on a second--
are you talking about
who I think
you're talking about?
The Monarch's Dogs
are looking for scraps, again?
They'll have to
get past us first.
[GOATEE] He can
send as many of his pets
as he wants,
makes no difference to us.
[SHAGA] Stop right there!
[SATO] Shaga?
[SHAGA] We need to talk.
[SATO] What? Is right
now really the time for this?
[SHAGA] No complaining!
[SATO] Shaga, come on!
What is wrong with you?
Okay, that was awkward.
So is he coming back?
[SATO] Then his real plan
is just to beat Yarizui?
So it would seem.
He wants to prove himself.
Or at least that's
what the retired
Wolf I talked to told me.
It turns out he's calling
himself the Monarch because he
wants to become the successor
to the Monarch Butterfly.
[SHAGA] You get it?
It's no coincidence
that he chose
that nom de guerre for himself.
We were wrong in thinking that
he wanted to conquer the West.
What he really wants is to
settle an old score by
defeating the Wizard's
successor, the Ice Witch.
But that's crazy.
[SHAGA] Anyway, you'd better go
warn her before it's too late.
We both know the
Monarch isn't afraid to
play dirty to get what he wants.
[SATO] She said she was
targeting his home turf.
She wanted to end this tonight,
so she left for
Ralph Store by herself.
What was she thinking?
[SATO] It's no use.
[DUDE 6A] I heard some
guys in the East were
beating up this girl in
front of the plaza.
It's screwed up!
[DUDE 6B] Dude, are you serious?
[DUDE 6C] Think we
should call the cops?
We're coming for ya.
[MALE ONLOOKER 6A]
What the hell was that?
All those guys
going after one girl?
Hey, what happened here?
Some gang dressed in
all black beat up a girl.
[SATO] Dressed in black?
Then that means.
[SHAGA] Yeah.
Gabriel Ratchet.
Damn Monarch.
[SHAGA] I'm an East Wolf,
which means the Ice Witch is
supposed to be my enemy,
but this is different.
I can't forgive them for this!
[MATSUBA] It's been a
while, hasn't it, Nikaido?
Oh.
Hey, Macchan.
Would you mind telling
me what this is all about?
I've heard the rumors,
but now I want the truth.
[NIKAIDO] Even if I did
tell you, then what?
You're not a Wolf
anymore, are you?
[MATSUBA] I suppose
asking for personal
reasons isn't
good enough, then?
Please, I think
I deserve to know.
Just tell me what
you're planning.
[NIKAIDO]
Look, I'm sorry but--
[MATSUBA] Nikaido,
what on earth did you do?
Of course.
So this is why you've
gathered everyone here.
All of Gabriel Ratchet
has come together to
show the strength
of the Eastern Territory.
But you're not hunting.
You're here to incite a war.
[MATSUBA] As you said,
I'm not a Wolf anymore.
I'm nothing but a
supermarket employee now,
and I can't do
anything to stop you.
However,
as a human being,
I despise you for doing this.
[ENDO] You've seen
better days, Ice Witch.
[YARIZUI] Even at my worst,
I'm better than you.
You're not a Wolf,
you're not even human.
Just a beast without
pride or shame.
[ENDO] Howl while
you can, Ice Witch.
Because once I defeat you,
this "beast" is going
to be a conqueror.
[ENDO] Let's see how long
that pride of yours lasts when
I've claimed the title
of the strongest
and you're groveling at my feet!
Stop it, this has gone
far enough, Monarch,
or should I just say Endo?
[NIKAIDO] Regardless of what
you say, I know that it isn't
your strength you're
trying to prove here.
It's freedom that you long for.
On the wings of a butterfly.
[MATSUBA]
Is that true, Nikaido?
[NIKAIDO] You know as well
as I do that this is pointless.
Even if you inherit her name,
nothing will change for
you or anyone else.
The Monarch Butterfly
is already gone!
[ENDO] Shut up!
What are you doing?
Forgive me, Macchan.
[MATSUBA] Nikaido, are you okay?
[ENDO] He's not your concern,
Goddess of Discounts!
Are you going to prepare
the half-price labels or not?
[MATSUBA THINKS] Why did
it have to turn out like this?
I'm sorry, but there's
nothing I can do.
You can take your
pride to the grave with you.
I'll bury you myself!
[SATO] Stop!
You've gone far
enough, Monarch!
[MALE VOICE 6A] Ben-To!
What are
you doing, Sato?
Didn't I tell you your job
was to protect the West?
[SATO] Oshiroi is there.
So are Brunette and Goatee.
Besides, if we didn't
come to help you,
what kinda friends would we be?
[SATO] And don't think I forgot.
You said it yourself, right?
You hate guys who stand by
and do nothing
when a girl is hurting.
[ENDO] You had me worried
for a second there, Ice Witch.
I actually thought someone
worthwhile was coming
to save you, not a
useless pair of weaklings.
You can say
what you want,
but the fact remains
that they're Wolves.
Do you understand, Monarch?
In other words,
someone who's not a Wolf,
who's not a Dog,
who's nothing but a filthy
rat has no room to talk.
How's that?
That's quite
a mouth you've got.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
[SHAGA] To you, obviously.
But if I was talking to a wall,
it'd make for better
conversation.
[weird noise]
[SATO] What's that noise?
You're kiddin' me!
[YARIZUI] Letting your
stomach do the talking, are you?
With the half price
bentos right in front of us,
there's no need for
words anymore.
That's fine. I'll beat
my message into you.
Our pride as Wolves
won't let us lose to a rat!
Treat others with respect,
and never lose your pride!
[ALL] Those are the
rules of this battlefield!
Attack!
We are the Wolves.
We uphold our rules and
put our pride on the line!
To the victor go eternal
glory and half-price bentos!
And to the defeated only
disgrace and hunger awaits!
[ENDO] You need
to learn your place!
[ENDO] How does it feel
to taste the power of a
man who's been
fasting for three days?
On this battlefield,
hunger isn't a weakness,
it's the source of our strength!
Only those who hunger
for victory ever grasp it.
And with my hunger at its
peak, my power is unparalleled.
Let's test that, shall we?
[YARIZUI] It doesn't matter
how long you fast when
your target isn't the
bento in the first place.
Gnash your teeth all you like,
but you're no Wolf if you
lose sight of your prey.
Feeling a little
sluggish, Monarch?
[YARIZUI] You're nothing
but a slobbering beast,
gazing longingly at
butterflies in the sky.
A prideless rat that can't rise
up from the muck that blinds it.
[ENDO] Shut up!
[ENDO] I am the Monarch!
The strongest Wolf that
has ever drawn breath!
Your hunger is shallow
and meaningless.
You have no focus,
no conviction, or pride.
Which means you have
no hope to defeat us!
[ENDO] Dammit!
Sato!
My leg!
This is the
hunger of a Wolf!
[SATO] Wow.
We really did it.
[SHAGA] Yeah. That wasn't
as bad as I thought.
[YARIZUI] I agree.
You did well, you two.
Hey, are you gonna
be able to make it home?
Of course. I'm fine, but I
think I'm going to pass on
fighting for the bento with
the seal this time around.
[SATO] Wow.
Well, what do you
think we should do?
Come on.
It's obvious!
It's mine.
You wish, buddy!
[OSHIROI] Yarizui, you're okay!
[YARIZUI] Oshiroi?
How are things in the West?
[OSHIROI] We did great!
I protected the shop
and got a bento!
I see.
Congratulations, then.
I grabbed one as well.
[OSHIROI]
I'd expect nothing less!
Oh, but where's Sato?
[SHAGA] Hey, be careful, you're
gonna spill the hot water!
[SATO] If you're gonna complain,
then walk on your own!
Oh, hey there, Oshiroi!
It was pretty tough this
time around, but here,
check this out.
I got the one
with the seal!
[MATSUBA] Finally awake?
[NIKAIDO] What happened?
How did the battle go?
[NIKAIDO] Endo.
[MATSUBA] After you
were knocked out,
some of the Ice Witch's
allies came to help her.
[NIKAIDO]
The Ice Witch's allies?
It was him.
That pervert, huh?
[MATSUBA] I'm sorry.
I suppose this is
something I should have
taken care of before
I retired as a Wolf.
[NIKAIDO] We did
this on our own.
It's our fault.
Please don't apologize.
It's time for you
to live your life freely now.
Gabriel Ratchet is disbanded.
But now, I'm nothing
but a lowly Dog.
I haven't earned the
freedom I've been granted.
[MATSUBA] Then like a
beast searching for a home,
go wherever the wind takes you.
I'm sure you'll find
your way soon enough.
I have faith in you.
Macchan.
[MATSUBA] Now go live your life.
[NIKAIDO] Right.
[NIKAIDO] Farewell.
Monarch Butterfly.
[SATO] Hey!
Cut it out! That's mine!
[SHAGA] Who cares?
You're not even hungry, right?
[SATO] Of course I am!
And besides, if you'd just asked
nicely, I'd let you have some!
[YARIZUI] Is that so?
Then I'll try some as well.
No. Not you,
too? Man.
I've actually never
tried zangee karaage before,
but it seems they marinate the
chicken longer than
the usual kind.
The flavor's truly exquisite.
Well, that's nice.
But between the two of you,
There's hardly any left for me.
[ALL] What a delicious meal!
[SHAGA] I ate so
much I got sleepy.
Hey, Shaga!
So, Sato, do you think
I'm a Wolf like you guys?
Hey, c'mon, what are
you talking about?
In the end, no matter
how hard I try,
it seems like you're
the one who always
ends up with the best bentos.
Also, I think I lose out to
the Ice Witch every time.
Whether you're
a Wolf or not...
You're something
different than just a Dog.
Something way more impressive.
Ya think so?
Uh-huh.
Seems like Oshiroi was
pretty amazing today, too.
Saito was held in
bondage by Shabriel Ratchet
when the Anarch came before him,
baring absolutely everything--
Jeez. I didn't think she
would fall asleep for real.
She fought pretty
hard back there.
Let her rest for a while.
'Kay.
The Beauty by the Lake.
I'm a little bit jealous.
It seems like she's already
become a wonderful Wolf.
[YARIZUI] What are
you talking about?
You two are no different.
Soon you'll have your very
own nom de guerre.
The same as her.
Do you think so?
My own title, huh?
Man, I sure hope I
end up with a cool one.
[SATO] This is
just the beginning.
I'll keep growing stronger.
I'll show my pride as a Wolf,
and earn my own legacy.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[GIRL VENDOR 6A]
Looks like Prize Number Eight.
[UCHIMOTO] Really Hawaiian.
[UCHIMOTO] There's no address.