[BENTO BRAWLER 4A]
Whoa, it's her!
[BENTO BRAWLER 4B]
She's beautiful!
[FEMALE CLERK 4A]
Thank you for shopping with us!
It's really her.
The Beauty.
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SATO] Have you heard the
cliché about a young man
waking up to find a
beautiful girl in his bed?
I didn't think that ever
happened in real life,
but here we are.
Too bad she's my cousin.
[SATO] Wait.
The hell is your problem?
Keep it down!
[SATO] My bad.
Sorry about that.
[SATO] Gotta go!
Back in the day you
only had a couple of these dirty
magazines and you tried
to keep them hidden
but you've got no shame now.
Looks like you've
gone full-blown perv.
Oh my goodness,
it's all so scandalous.
[SATO] Stop!
They're not mine, all right?
This kid named Uchimoto
keeps giving 'em to me.
Well, just cause
you're a horn-ball
doesn't mean
I don't love ya, cuz.
[Sato groans]
What the heck are you
doing in my dorm room anyway?
Hang on, lemme
warm up first.
[clears her throat]
C'mere you!
That hurt.
Tell me something.
How did we get like this?
I just don't understand how
I ended up in the friend zone.
And I don't understand
how warming up your voice
is related to what you're
trying to do right now.
Yeah, good point!
So, what's
goin' on anyway?
What made you come
all the way here?
Well, I came
because I wanna
know how I ended
up in the friend--
[SATO] All right.
That's enough, Shaga.
You've gotta at least
try a different tactic.
Now why're you here?
See, the
friend zone isn't--
[SATO] This is pointless.
C'mon, just
one more time!
I'm gonna say 'no.'
Why not?
It's funny!
No, it is not.
Geez.
You're such a tool.
[Shaga laughs]
[SHAGA] How 'bout we
play a game instead?
[SHAGA] Hey!
Where's Virtual-on?
[SATO] Back at home.
My Dad couldn't live without it.
[SHAGA] Oh wow,
you have Space Harrier!
Let's play that one!
[SHAGA] Is that
the best you can do?
Man, I can't believe how
bad you suck at this game!
[SHAGA] Well,
that was fun. All right!
How about we play some
Virtua 2 and call it a day?
Y'know, I feel like
I'm forgetting something
but I have no idea
what could it be.
Well, I guess it's gone.
Hold on, I just
remembered what it was!
Do you mind if
I sit up here with you?
Well, no but--
[SHAGA] Listen, I have a
really big favor to ask you.
[SATO] Can't it wait?
No way! Is this
some kinda sick joke?
Please, just say yes.
Yeah right,
when pigs fly!
Oh, okay.
Suit yourself then.
I guess we'll have
to make a bet!
One single match,
winner takes all.
If I beat ya, you do what
I asked no matter what.
And as for the other
possible outcome here.
[SHAGA] If I lose,
you can touch me.
Anywhere you like.
No thanks.
You're stubborn,
that's for sure.
Well, we're both high schoolers
now, so I don't see why not.
I'll take off my clothes first.
What?
No way!
Or you could slip
your hand under my bra?
You think that'll do the trick?
[VIDEO GAME VOICE] Excellent!
Yeah, I won!
Come on, Mommy.
[SATO] I'm sorry to call
you on a Sunday like this.
[OSHIROI] It's no
big deal. Really.
[SATO] Do you always wear
your uniform on weekends?
Oh no.
First, I couldn't decide what
to wear, then I ran out of time
trying stuff on, so I
ended up stuck with this.
[SATO] Not a bad choice.
Thanks. Right.
I brought this.
Although I'm
not quite sure
what you want
with a girl's uniform.
[SATO] Thank you so much.
I'm hoping it fits okay
but I wouldn't be surprised
if it was a little loose
in the chest area, because I'm
not anywhere near as big as you.
[Oshiroi gasps]
He must want to get in
touch with his feminine side.
I knew it!
[OSHIROI] You want it,
go right ahead!
It's yours!
Please, use it as
much as you want!
[SATO] Talk about weird.
I wonder what Shaga
wants with this uniform.
[SATO] I have a really
bad feeling about this.
[SATO] Good mornin' ladies.
[SATO] And I was right.
Oh hey there, cuz.
Well, this
is a surprise.
Why didn't you bother
to tell me your cousin is
the Beauty by the Lake?
Wait, hold on a second.
Beauty by the what?
Time out.
Does that mean you're a Wolf?
Is that what they call you?
[YARIZUI]
Your reputation precedes you.
I knew I would have
to face you eventually.
If someone like me steps
foot on another crew's turf,
you know that means war, right?
You versus me in a one-on-one.
Whaddaya say, Ice Witch?
Fine then.
I'll see you at the
Ho-ki Mart tonight.
[SHAGA] Oh! I just
love those plump little
breasts of yours,
but why are you
hiding them underneath
that nasty old bra?
[SHAGA] Your skin is so soft!
[SATO] Uh, Shaga?
[SHAGA]
Let's take a bath together!
[SATO] Whoa!
Can you teach me how to do that?
So tell me
something Sato,
is she normally like this
or has she gone insane?
Didn't they teach you
that no means no?
Not only
is she adorable,
but she's as lively as
a spring chicken in heat!
Hey Sato, do you
wanna feel her up, too?
Actually, believe
it or not,
this behavior's
pretty typical for her.
[OSHIROI] Let go!
Please!
I have so much work
left to do on my novel!
[SHAGA] Well, I have something
you can work on right here!
That's it.
Work me up!
This is Oshiroi.
Yes, that's right.
Yes. Uh, I am.
I'm coming right now!
Ah man, she got away.
[SATO] Hey, Shaga.
How come you never told
me you were a Wolf before?
Whaddya say we take a peek
at this little novel of hers?
Shall we?
Don't be like that;
respect her privacy!
[SHAGA] "Muscle Cop."
[SHAGA] "A thrilling story
of the serial murder
of high school
girls in the city.
The rookie cop Saito dons
his ill-fitting, awkwardly tight
school girls' uniform and
infiltrates the
suspect's hideout."
"However Monk,
the dastardly perpetrator,
can easily see
through Saito's disguise."
Saito, huh?
And Monk's in there?
You take over Ice Witch,
I'm getting bored with this.
"Wait a second, I'm not
really a high school girl".
"I know, Saito. I've waited
for you for so long."
"Stop it, take
your hands off me".
Oh my.
"What's the matter big boy,
is this your first
time or something?"
So is this type
of thing
popular with the kids nowadays?
They're gonna
eat you alive!
Get up! get back
out there and fight!
I've got faith in you!
He's getting in touch
with his feminine side!
I knew it!
[SATO] Crap, it's Shiraume!
[SHIRAUME] What did
you do to Oshiroi?
[OSHIROI] Sato!
Run for your life!
[SHIRAUME]
Start talking!
You'd better spill it
or I will hurt you.
[SATO] I'm not the
one at fault, trust me.
[SHAGA] Hey, why'd you go
and put your bra back on?
You want me to take
it off again, dontcha?
[OSHIROI] No!
Please let me go!
See, what'd I tell ya?
So you're the one
who's responsible for all this!
Hold up, what?
[SHIRAUME] Do you
go to our school?
I've never seen you before.
I'm a first year at
Marutomi University High.
The name's Ayame Shaga.
[SHIRAUME] I see.
Where'd you get
this uniform, Shaga?
I borrowed it from
your adorable friend here.
Sato got it for me.
[SHIRAUME] I see. Once again,
your insolence has left
me with no other
choice in the matter!
Suck on that.
Hopefully next time he'll know
not to act like such a tool.
But the question remains,
what do I do with you?
I'd mess up your pretty hair,
but you beat me to it.
Oh stop.
[SHIRAUME] For your own sake,
I demand that you take
a bath immediately.
[SHAGA] Wait, what?
[SHIRAUME] Do you prefer
your bathwater warm?
Or hot?
Hey, wait a second,
don't you think
maybe we should
discuss this first?
Man, that girl is scary.
[ENDO] Gimme a
status report.
[NIKAIDO] Yes, sir.
I've gathered all the
intel I can find on
Wolves in the Western Territory
with a nom de guerre .
The only thing we have
to worry about now is her.
The Beauty by the Lake.
[ENDO] Ayame Shaga.
[MALE VOICE 4A] Ben-To!
[SATO] Hello? What?
[SHAGA] You have to come quick!
Hurry! Or Mistress Shiraume
will find me!
Mistress Shiraume?
Just perfect.
[SHAGA] I'm over here!
[SATO] Shaga?
[SHAGA] Took you long enough!
Hey. What's
with the frilly dress?
And you smell nice, like flowery
bath soap or something.
[SHIRAUME] Just remember,
I'm doing this for your own
good, do you understand?
Besides, after what you did to
Oshiroi you deserve it.
I did nothing wrong,
I was only trying to forge
some bonds with a little
female contact, that's all.
Yes, of course.
Here's an idea.
Why don't we forge
some bonds of our own?
How about a little
female contact with me?
Wow, that hurt.
Hey, hold on!
Wait!
My little Shaga.
Hey, let's
talk about this
before we do anything
crazy. Okay?
You can run but you
can't hide, my pretty.
Huh?
I want you to trust me,
darling, I've done this a
thousand times
so there's nothing
for you to be worried about.
Yeah, right.
How does this feel?
[SHAGA] Get off me!
[SHAGA] You expect
me to wear this thing?
[SHIRAUME] Of course, I
think you'd look perfect in it.
Here, let me help you put it on.
Well, I'd say
you're pretty lucky,
you managed to get
away unscathed.
[SHAGA] I want to die.
Look, don't be silly.
It looks nice on ya.
I'd think you'd be
more into fashion.
I mean, since you're
half-Italian and all.
I know you're just trying
to make me feel better.
I have to distract
myself so I don't keep
remembering the terrible
events that just transpired.
But how?
Sato!
What time is it?
So you showed up.
Does someone
wanna tell me
what's up with the dress?
It's kind of
a long story,
it's better to just
leave it alone.
That's fine by me.
I didn't really wanna
know anyway.
Tell me, Sato, which
bento are you going after?
[SATO] The Japanese
style tofu burger.
[SHAGA] I thought, as a
general rule, members of the
Half-Price Food Lovers club
don't go for the same dish?
[SATO] Yeah, so?
Don't tell me that you're
gonna go after that one, too.
No way.
You take it; I'll grab the
ginger fried pork bento instead.
[SHAGA] What's wrong?
Are we going after the
same dish, Ice Witch?
[door opens]
[SHAGA] So, that's
the Beefy God, huh?
I see you did
your homework.
Yeah, I know a thing or
two about the shops in the west.
So?
[YARIZUI] Where do
you get your intel?
Listen up.
Yes, ma'am.
The number of
half-priced bentos
to Wolves is
extremely low tonight.
And these guys aren't
exactly pushovers either.
So bring your 'A Game.'
[SATO] Yeah.
I gotcha.
[SATO] Hey!
What the heck do
you think you're doing?
[NIKAIDO] Let's rock and roll.
[SHAGA]
What's with the Ice Witch?
She's a cold-hearted
Wolf, isn't she?
Definitely lives up
to her nom de guerre.
[SATO] I guess so.
Just save yourself the
trouble and give up.
Oh please...
Your lame attempt
at cracking jokes
is as pathetic as it ever was.
Hey, that wasn't a joke.
Wait!
[SATO] Damn, I'm late!
[YARIZUI] Bring it on.
[SATO] Shaga!
Are you all right?
I told you this was a bad idea!
[SHAGA] I'm perfectly fine.
Haven't you ever heard the old
adage "whatever doesn't
kill you only makes you
stronger in the end"?
I would say that applies to her.
And I'd say you've
completely lost
touch with reality.
The Ice Witch may
have beaten me this time.
But trust me, this isn't
even close to being over.
From the harsh jaws of defeat,
I will snatch victory.
Go get a bento and
give it to me afterwards,
then once you do,
you'll have your reward.
A big hug from me!
[YARIZUI] You're pretty
good, but it's hard
to take you
seriously in that getup.
Still, you're not nearly
good enough to beat me!
Wait, what?
[YARIZUI] We stand on a
battlefield for half-price food,
but you're so focused.
you only have eyes for me.
[YARIZUI] You may be strong,
but if you don't keep the
food in mind, then it's
just senseless violence.
You can't
win like that.
You still have
a lot to learn, Beauty.
Please understand
that I don't hate you.
[SATO] Shaga!
[YARIZUI] Never give up.
[YARIZUI] To get what
you want, you have to
focus on what matters most.
I have to focus
on what matters most.
[stomach growls]
Oh no, you don't!
I get what I want!
[SATO THINKS] This guy
is nuts! He's so strong!
But I don't care.
Defeat is not an option!
[SATO] Spinach seasoned
with soy sauce,
served with veggies and rice.
The vibrant colors
are bright enough to
rival the flowers of
a holiday wreath!
[SATO] Wait a sec!
Is that tofu burger handmade?
You gotta be kiddin' me!
And are those maitake
mushrooms served in bean paste?
Jackpot!
I didn't even know
it had mushrooms!
That bento is all mine!
[FEMALE CLERK 4B] Thank
you, please come again!
You got it, congratulations.
[SATO] Yeah.
Sure did.
[YARIZUI] Who was that guy?
He's definitely not
from around here.
[SHAGA] Next time you
won't be so lucky, Ice Witch.
[SATO] Shaga.
[YARIZUI] If you ever
wanna give it another shot,
you know where you
can find me, Beauty.
C'mon Sato,
we should get going;
I'm absolutely starved.
Sorry Shaga, but I'm
gonna eat in the club room.
[YARIZUI] You're welcome
to join us, if you want to.
[SHAGA] No, thanks.
[SATO] Man, I wonder
what's wrong with her.
[YARIZUI] You should probably
go eat with her, Sato.
[SATO] Oh, whatever,
she'll be fine.
I remember when we were little
kids and they'd give us animal
crackers at school she would
always throw a huge fit
just like this whenever she
didn't get an elephant.
[YARIZUI] Just go.
I can't stand guys who ignore
girls when they're hurting.
She needs somebody
to talk to right now.
Lemme ask you this,
if I was the one crying
and not her,
would you try to help me,
or would you stand there
doing nothing like a coward?
[SATO] Good advice.
[ENDO] Interesting.
In that case,
I think it's best we put the
plan into action before
they make their move.
[NIKAIDO] But,
it's possible that rivalry
might hurt us as well, boss.
[ENDO] So what?
Why should I care about a bunch
of Wolves in sheep's clothing?
[SATO] Seriously.
Would you quit pouting, Shaga?
The truth is,
I'm ticked off at you,
but I'm also mad at myself.
Let's settle this now!
Rock-paper-scissors
to determine who's responsible.
Do we have a deal?
I'll take rock;
so do the right thing!
[SHAGA] Okay, rock,
paper, scissors.
Go!
[SATO] Sorry.
[SHAGA] Now say
it ten more times.
[SATO] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
How many do I have left?
Twenty more to go.
[SATO] The hell?
[SHAGA]
Shut up, moron.
No! That was the best
bite in the whole box!
It's delicious.
Oh, Sato.
I almost forgot to
give you your reward.
Um, what are you doing?
Did you forget our deal?
Your bento box in exchange
for a big hug, remember?
Yeah, I do.
[SHAGA]
This is a little awkward,
so why don't you hurry
up and get it over with?
Come on.
'Kay.
[SHAGA] Tell me something,
how did we get like this?
I just don't understand how
I ended up in the friend zone.
[SATO] You're joking, right?
Let it go already.
[SHAGA] Fine, I will.
[SHAGA] Sato, can I
tell you something?
[SATO] Yeah, sure.
[SHAGA] Never mind.
[SATO] What?
[SHAGA] It's not important.
[SATO] You have to tell me now.
[SHAGA] Just-- Just
forget about it, okay?
[SATO] Ugh.
That is so not cool.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[YARIZUI] "Please stop!
No, don't stop!
Wait, that's not the right spot,
that's the wrong oh, oh-- oh!"
"Saito was overwhelmed
by his desire to get
down on his knees even
though he didn't want to.
On next week's episode
of Muscle Cop,
when ripped muscles of steel
are covered in salty sweat,
the taste of betrayal
tears him apart."
What?
That's the wrong script?