[SHAGA] Check it out!
Allow me to blow your minds.
Ta-da!
[SATO] What're those?
[SHAGA] I was talking with
Matsuba at Ralph Store
yesterday and
she gave them to me.
She told me to share
them with you guys.
[SATO] They're free tickets
to the Super Hawaiian Park.
What's that?
[YARIZUI] A water park.
And everything's indoors.
It's run by the same company
that owns the Ralph Store chain.
[SATO THINKS] A water park?
That means swimsuits!
[YARIZUI] You okay?
What's the deal?
[SATO] We have to do this!
[YARIZUI] Sure,
it sounds pretty fun.
[SATO] Great!
Thank you!
[SATO THINKS] Summer just
began, and I already get
to see Yarizui
in a bathing suit.
I am the happiest man
on the face of the earth!
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SATO] Geez.
I didn't realize we'd have
to travel so far to get there.
[SHAGA] It's just
a two hour train ride,
and it'll totally be worth it.
I brought some snacks
if you're starting
to get hungry.
[SATO] Thanks,
but that's not the problem.
It's just train tickets
are freakin' expensive.
[SHAGA] Why're you so cheap?
[SATO] It's not like I wanna be!
I've barely got enough
to get by each month.
[SHAGA] A cheap
excuse for a cheap guy.
Yeah, sorry I couldn't
afford to buy you train
tickets on top
of the free passes
I gave you to the water park.
[SATO] No,
that's not what I meant!
Just think about all the
fun you're going to have today!
The place is huge so
I'm sure you'll have
your hands full
exploring it all.
[SATO THINKS]
I'll have my hands full?
They're definitely
a hand full. Oh yeah.
Hey, cut it out!
Yarizui is more than enough!
[SATO THINKS] I wonder what
kind of swimsuit she wears.
A bikini?
One piece?
Maybe a school swimsuit?
Whatever, the cut
doesn't really matter.
She's gonna be clad
in a single, skimpy,
thin layer and that's priceless.
That's more than enough to make
up for the cost
of the train ride.
Yes.
I would spend all
the money I have
just to see her in a swimsuit!
[YARIZUI] I win.
There's no beating
the president, guys.
What?
That bites!
I really thought I had a chance
there, but I'm second place!
Dang it!
Of course I had to
get stuck with the joker.
At least I'm in third.
Awww!
You're the Lowest Dirt!
That's too bad!
[SATO] What the--?
How'd this even happen?
I've got like a
million cards left.
Well, maybe you
should've concentrated
on getting rid of 'em
instead of fantasizing.
I'm less than
impressed with
your inability to
focus on the battle.
[SATO] You want
focus, let's go again!
[SHAGA] Okay fine, round two!
It's your shuffle, genius!
[SATO] Yeah, I'm aware of that.
[SHAGA] Whoever's the
Lowest Dirt this round has
to carry everyone's
bags when we get there!
All right, which one
of you ladies
packed something
ridiculously heavy?
Oh, that would
be me, I'm really sorry.
I couldn't make this trip
without my laptop, and I had to
bring my Oxford Dictionary
and my favorite anatomy book.
[SATO] Why would you need
all that at a water park?
'Cause my novel.
Detective Saito is lured to a
water park with free tickets
only to encounter a serial
killer who targets lifeguards,
but the detective
falls prey to his
evil scheme and is
publicly disgraced.
Well, that's the plotline
I was tinkering
with late last night anyway.
But that's pretty much
all I've got for now so
obviously I had to
come prepared just
in case inspiration strikes me.
[SATO] You couldn't just
pack a pen and notepad?
And why do you
need an anatomy book?
[SHAGA] I'm missing a ticket.
That's really weird, I must've
dropped it somewhere on the way.
Oh well, I guess
it's not like we can go
search the train for
it or anything.
Somebody's gotta pay.
Wait, you don't mean--
Sorry, I don't have
any more passes.
I'm using my
employee card to get in.
[SATO] Take your bags at least!
[SATO] This sucks!
After I pay for the train home
I'm only gonna have
three hundred yen left.
Talk about the Lowest Dirt.
[NIKAIDO] Pervert?
[NIKAIDO] This is the last place
I expected to run into you.
Just my luck.
Y'know,
I'd really appreciate it
if you'd stop
calling me Pervert!
Would you stop
following me, Pervert?
This is the entrance,
we're both going inside,
and don't ever call
me that again, okay?
Hey! Nikaido!
I'm so glad you
could make it out!
Yeah.
What're you looking at?
I'm just surprised
that you act so normal.
Look, how many
times do I have to
tell you I'm not a pervert?
Whatever. Doesn't matter
if you are or not
you're still stuck with
it as your nom de guerre.
[SATO] Huh?
Listen man, I know you get
a kick outta messin' with me,
but don't make
any jokes about my--
It's not a joke.
I spread the
name around already.
Wait; hold on
a sec, you did what?
[OSHIROI] Cut it out!
What're you doing?
Please stop pinching me!
Especially there!
Hey. That sounds like
Oshiroi's voice.
[SHAGA] Oh calm down,
you know you like it!
Wow!
Look how pink they are!
They're just begging
to be pinched!
What the hell're
you doing, Pervert?
I'm harnessing the power
of my mind to see through walls.
[SHAGA] Damn, Matsuba!
Your clothes really hide
those ginormous ta-tas.
[MATSUBA] Ya think so?
Well I've gotta reserve the
goods for my husband.
[SHAGA] I bet you
grope 'em all the
time to make 'em bigger, huh?
[MATSUBA] You might wanna
borrow Oshiroi's anatomy book.
[SHAGA] Really, Ice Witch?
You wore your swimsuit under
your clothes the whole way here?
That's so middle school.
[YARIZUI] It's a
time saving measure.
[SHAGA] What's wrong?
[YARIZUI] I forgot my
spare pair of underwear.
[SHAGA] I guess you're goin'
commando on the way home.
[YARIZUI] Looks like it.
[YARIZUI] Wait, here they are.
[steel drum music playing]
Geez, whaddya think's
taking them so long?
[SHAGA] Sato!
We're over here! Hey!
[OSHIROI] Look!
We locked down the perfect spot!
[SATO] Oh, cool.
Thanks, great job.
[Sato groans]
[SATO] I can see so
much skin. I'm dyin' here.
[YARIZUI] What's the deal?
Why are you staring at me?
You're not about to make fun of
me for stretching, are you?
No, of course not.
Don't be ridiculous!
[YARIZUI] Oh,
so now I'm ridiculous?
[SATO] I didn't mean
it like that, Yarizui!
[MATSUBA] Oh, good.
You all found each other.
I'm gonna go hang out
in the café over there for a
little while, so try not
to get in any trouble.
[YARIZUI] Well. Let's go.
Come on, follow me, Sato!
[SATO] Uh, yeah!
[OSHIROI] Right behind you!
[SHAGA] Wait for me!
[SATO] Got it!
[Oshiroi giggles]
[SATO] Good job, loser.
[SATO] Sorry, excuse me.
"Hyoketsu Ice", huh?
I wonder if she--
Nah, that can't be it.
Saito had a
weird feeling.
[SATO] Hey Yarizui?
I was just wondering,
how'd you wind
up with Ice Witch
as your nom de guerre?
[SATO] Uh, I'm sorry. If
you're not comfortable talking
about it just forget
I ever asked.
[YARIZUI] No,
it's not a big deal.
I'd rather you hear
it from me anyway.
[YARIZUI] Well, you see,
it's kind of embarrassing,
but I got the name
my freshman year.
After a brawl, I went to
pay for my half-price bento
and I tried to buy a can of
Hyoketsu Ice along with it.
[SATO] Really?
[YARIZUI] Calm down.
I wasn't trying to buy booze.
I only grabbed it
'cuz it was on sale
and I liked the can's design.
I thought it was some
new flavored water.
[SATO] Uh, okay.
[YARIZUI]
It's not like I drank it.
The cashier didn't
even let me buy it.
I was wearing my uniform
so it was obvious
I was too young to drink.
Okay guys, do you
have to look at me like that?
Look at you like what?
So, how 'bout you, Shaga?
The whole 'Beauty
by the Lake' thing.
I'm sure there's gotta be an
interesting story behind that.
Whoa!
Way to put a girl
on the spot, Sato!
[SATO] You don't wanna
talk about yours either?
I just don't understand
why you're
asking me about
this all of a sudden.
Y'know you have to allow a girl
to keep some secrets to herself.
If you really wanna
know, it's because she ate
her first half-price bento in
Lake Park and as soon as she
was done eating
she passed out
on the bench until
the next morning.
Hey, did you
have to tell him?
Wow, noms de guerre
seem kinda mean, huh?
Yeah.
I was expecting
some cool back story.
[NIKAIDO] Well, it's not
like yours is that cool.
[YARIZUI] I didn't know Sato
has a nom de guerre now.
What is it?
Just ignore him! Don't
listen to anything he says!
[announcement tones]
[PARK ANNOUNCER 7A] Aloha!
Thanks for visiting us today!
We now have a variety of
bento boxes ready to sell.
Come on by the poolside
café and enjoy a bite to eat!
How can I help you?
[YARIZUI] Alright.
[SHAGA] I wonder.
[SATO] Oh, man, food.
[Sato's stomach growls]
[SATO THINKS] This sucks.
With the way my luck is
going today, it's pretty damn
doubtful they're gonna
offer any discounts.
[Oshiroi's stomach growls]
[SATO] Sounds like
I'm not the only one.
Of course you're here.
I figured you might come.
Well, it's not
like we could turn
down a personal
invitation from Macchan.
[BRUNETTE] For real.
How could we say no to her?
[VENDOR 7A] Yo!
We've got your new
vending machines.
[ASEBI] I made it!
Good thing I rolled off
that truck and woke up!
I sure hope this
free ticket's still valid
and they'll actually let me in.
[SHAGA] Ben-To.
Does it feel
tense to you guys?
Hey, look who's
over there, Saito.
I'm sorry, I mean, Sato!
[SATO] What're they doing here?
Hold on.
That can only mean one thing.
[YARIZUI] Exactly.
The park's owned
by Ralph Store,
so they mark down
their bento here, too.
Yeah. What, you
really didn't know that?
It's why this
place is so popular.
They offer half-price food
specials every Sunday
starting one hour before
closing the water park.
[Oshiroi's stomach growls]
[Sato's stomach growls]
[SATO THINKS] Awesome.
I've still got a chance of
getting my stomach to shut up.
They're rolling out
the discount cart right now.
Looks like those're
the half-price deals.
[SATO] I think I've seen
those bentos before.
[MATSUBA] Yeah, it wouldn't
surprise me if you have.
Since the park's
affiliated with Ralph Store,
it's stocked with the same food.
[OSHIROI] There are a couple of
'em I don't recognize though.
[SHAGA]
"Loco Moco Bulging Bento"?
That one's gotta be exclusive
to the water park, huh?
[MATSUBA] It's influenced
by Hawaiian cuisine,
but modified for
Japanese sensibilities.
It's basically hamburger
patties on rice.
It comes with a fruit
salad and you scoop it
off into the lid, and then you
just microwave the meal.
[OSHIROI] Yeah, that's
sounding pretty delicious to me.
[MATSUBA] It is.
The other box they're offering
is the Bosomelet Bento.
It was actually
selected from a recipe
contest amongst Ralph
Store employees.
They're doing an early
release for it in the
area to see what people think.
Not to brag or anything,
but it's my recipe.
Their marketing people came up
with the silly name though.
There are two different flavors
of fried rice hidden beneath
the omelet and lining the tray,
and I added just a dash of
condensed milk to the omelet,
so it has quite the
unique flavor to it.
[YARIZUI] Oh really?
Consider me enticed.
[MATSUBA] I think the Loco
Moco Bulging bento is gonna
get the laurel wreath seal,
but I stand by my
Bosomelet recipe and
I highly recommend it.
[YARIZUI]
Thanks for the heads up.
So what do you guys think?
Have you all decided
on your prey yet?
[SATO] Look! Here comes
the God of Discounts!
[OSHIROI] Oh, man.
I wonder what he's like.
[SHAGA] Really?
That's him?
Hey, what's that?
[SATO] He's putting
the food in the pool?
[MATSUBA] Those are Super Fresh
Balls, they're specifically
designed to allow bento brawls
to take place in the pool.
They're still determining
their practicality.
It seems like
it would make
the battle more unpredictable.
With the motion of the water,
you never know what to expect.
[SATO] Yeah, good point.
Regardless.
No matter what
situation we might face.
We will do battle
as proud wolves!
[ALL] And we will
take what we desire!
There's no running by
the poolside, okay you guys?
[ASEBI] Wow!
It's a beach ball with
some kind of food inside!
Ow! That hurts!
Why are my legs
cramping up on me?
[BENTO BRAWLER 7B]
The chlorine's killing my eyes!
Perfect, now's
my chance!
[BRUNETTE] You're chasing the
laurel wreath seal again, huh?
You've gotten pretty ambitious
lately, haven't you, Pervert?
So he wasn't just
messing with me,
that's really my
nom de guerre?
I thought you knew.
Everybody else does.
Sorry but you're
stuck with it, pal.
You're The Pervert now!
It's mine now!
[SATO THINKS]
No! Don't look!
Think of something else!
Anything!
Resist the temptation if you
wanna be able to move!
It's hopeless!
[SHAGA] Sato!
[SATO] Shaga?
[SHAGA] Poor Sato.
You looked like you were
having a hard time moving,
so I thought I'd help you out.
[NIKAIDO] It's right there!
You can do this, man!
I want that bosomelet
in my mouth!
[NIKAIDO] It's mine!
Macchan created that dish,
so I wanna be the one
who feasts upon it!
I have to!
[MATSUBA] A dash
of condensed milk!
[NIKAIDO] I have to!
[MATSUBA] Fried rice!
[NIKAIDO] I have to--
I am less
than impressed
with your inability to
focus on the battle.
Am I helping?
Damn it!
[SHAGA] Really?
Don't tell me you're
already dropping out?
[SHAGA] Hey!
That's mine, dammit!
Hey, are you alright?
Ya sound like you're havin' a
hard time catchin' your breath.
[SHAGA] You're one to talk.
--Holy crap!
--You've gotta be kidding me!
[GOATEE] He must be using the
wall jets for
maximum propulsion!
[SHAGA] How is he that agile?
[GOATEE] It's like he's got
a rudder between his legs!
Did you just
say a rudder?
There's no way.
It can't be that big!
[SHAGA] He's almost to it!
He actually got it!
I did it! I got
the laurel wreath seal!
[SHAGA] Well.
There's his rudder.
The Loco Moco Bulging
bento's all mine!
Look at it!
It's huge!
[SATO] Oh yeah!
I am the man!
Uh.
Hey. Sato?
Yeah, and he says
he's not a pervert.
[SATO] No!
You want me to heat that up?
[YARIZUI] Yes, please.
What the hell?
No, no, no. No! Oh no.
Oh no!
[SHIRAUME] Hello, Sato.
Oh great, what the heck
are you doing here, Shiraume?
That's really your biggest
concern right now?
What strikes me as the biggest
issue at hand is the fact that
you're exposing yourself
to the entire water park,
and more
specifically, to Oshiroi.
[SATO] Look, it's not like
I meant for this to happen!
Where'd she--
[SHIRAUME]
Go put some clothes on.
[UCHIMOTO] Wooo!
[SHIRAUME] I'm terribly
sorry you had to see that.
C'mon, it'll be okay.
[SATO] Oh man, that
hurt but it was worth it.
[YARIZUI] Nicely done, Sato.
I can't believe I missed your
moment of victory, though.
I wish I could've seen it.
[SATO] Honestly,
it's probably for the
best that you weren't around.
[YARIZUI] And why's that?
[SATO] Uh, anyway, check it out.
Another seal for the book!
Awesome.
[YARIZUI] We better
make sure we don't lose it
before we get back
to the club room.
Here.
I've got an idea.
Why did you do that?
It's gonna be tough
for you to lose it now.
[SATO] Huh?
Are you serious?
[YARIZUI] When am I not?
Okay, Yarizui,
if you insist.
[SHAGA] Oh, come on.
Are you really gonna
show it off like that?
[SATO] I see you
got a bento, too.
Yep. It was just floating
around out there and
nobody seemed to notice it,
so I swam over and grabbed it.
[YARIZUI] Funny
how it works out.
Yet another reason these
brawls are so interesting.
Well, then.
What're we waiting for,
let's dig in.
[SATO] Right!
[ALL]
Thank you for the meal!
[YARIZUI] Let's see.
Wow.
She wasn't kidding.
This really is a unique omelet.
It has such a rich flavor to it.
The fried rice is
seasoned with vinegar
so it complements
the eggs nicely.
[SATO] Mind if I have a bite?
[YARIZUI]
Not at all. Go for it.
[SHAGA] Me too!
I want one of your patties!
[SATO] I would've given you
a bite, but not half of it!
Oh my gosh, the sauce
on it is so tangy and delicious!
No wonder it got the seal!
You're sharin'
your pork with me!
No way!
[SATO] Hand it over, dammit!
I thought you
wanted a bite?
[SATO] Yes, I do!
Thank you!
[MATSUBA] Hey Nikaido?
I made this before
we left earlier today
but I can't eat
it all by myself.
You wanna share?
I'd love to!
Oh, wow.
Those're some
succulent bosomelets!
[SATO] Alright, Yarizui.
I guess we should pack up.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
This place has everything
you could ask for.
Hey, is there something
wrong, Beauty?
Oh, it's nothing really.
I could've sworn I saw
Asebi during the brawl
but I must've confused
her with somebody else.
That is by far the most
fun I've ever had in a sew--
Well, whatever...
We should prob'ly hurry up
and get to the preview.
Really? Is it that
time again already?
What's it
gonna be about?
The touch of evil
reaches out for Sato
after he suffers an
unfortunate accident.
And the episode's highlight?
The characters
briefly introduced
today will get more screen time.
And you can count on that!
Just watch it.