[FEMALE STUDENT 3A]
So how did everything go?
[FEMALE STUDENT 3B] Not so good.
[FEMALE STUDENT 3C]
I found an awesome
fro-yo shop the other day!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3D] Oh yeah?
Where is it?
[girls gasp]
[ALL GIRLS]
Good morning, Coach Dandou!
[YAMAHARA]
Hey, did you guys hear?
[KENDO CLUB A]  'Bout what?
You mean, the streaker who ran
around campus and then
jumped into the incinerator?
I heard that.
[KENDO CLUB B] I betcha
he was a hippy who was tryin'
to protest the burning of trash.
[KENDO CLUB A] Nah man, they
just tie themselves to stuff.
[KENDO CLUB C] Hold up!
Do you think it
could've been an alien?
[KENDO CLUB D]
Get a life, dumbass!
What I heard was--
[KENDO CLUB E] Um, excuse me?
[KENDO CLUB F] Yeah?
What is it, Freshman?
[KENDO CLUB E] I heard
someone threw a school uniform
out the window and
the student council,
who were out collecting trash,
added it to the pile
they were gonna burn.
Apparently, the guy
who'd lost his uniform
jumped into the
incinerator to get it back.
[KENDO CLUB ALL]
Yeah, right.
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[giggles and gasps]
[SHIRAUME]
Would you mind telling me
where your
cell phone is, Sato?
Huh?
My phone?
Uh, but why?
[SHIRAUME] Tell me
where it is right now or
I'll be forced to
search you for it.
Seriously?
Wait!
Yeah, I remember
where it is now!
I left it in my dorm room!
[SATO] I'm telling the truth!
Tell her I'm not lying!
[SATO] Hey! Don't just
turn your backs on me!
And you are?
Aw, crap.
What was the big
guy's name again?
Quasimodo?
No, that's not it.
Uchi.
Uchimoto!
Hey, thanks, I really
owe ya one, buddy.
My advice to you is just
enjoy what's about to happen.
I know I would.
[SATO] Huh?
[Sato screams]
[YARIZUI] You're telling me
she did this to you because
you wouldn't give
her your cell phone?
Yeah, she totally
embarrassed me
in front of the whole class.
When she pulled
my uniform off me,
the zipper on my pants ripped.
Well, in that case.
Take 'em off.
C'mon, let's go.
I don't have all day.
[SATO] But this is
all so sudden.
I mean, it's just
that I've never
done it before, y'know?
I'm just fixing
your zipper, perv.
[SATO] I knew that.
[YARIZUI] I might
as well fix the top
button on your
shirt while I'm at it.
Take that off, too.
Geez, would you
quit staring at me like that?
Who, me?
I wasn't staring, I swear!
[YARIZUI] Of the different
types of half-price bento,
sushi are the
hardest to find.
And why's that?
[YARIZUI] I'm sure you're
aware sushi bentos are
the most expensive
at the supermarket.
Even at half-price,
they're still pretty costly.
And they tend to go bad faster.
They're also very
popular so
they sell-out before
the end of the day.
[SATO] What do you mean "only"?
I don't want you takin' any!
[OSHIROI] Just a
couple for research?
Hey Sato,
are you even listening?
[SATO] Uh.
Not really.
I'm sorry. Would you
mind if we talked about
all this once I got my
clothes back on?
Sorry but I'm feelin'
a little overexposed.
[SATO] No, my uniform!
What the hell?
[YARIZUI] Now that your uniform
isn't around to distract you,
what do you say we continue
our conversation, Sato?
Wait, what was I
talking about again?
Oh yeah sushi.
So it's basically a meal
that consists of mostly--
I know what sushi is!
[knock at door]
Nice boxers, perv.
This is all your fault.
You should've just
handed over your phone.
[SHIRAUME]
I apologize for jumping
to conclusions last night.
Oshiroi explained
everything and
it all makes perfect
sense to me now.
I don't understand why
anyone would fight over food.
However, I am thrilled to
know that these battles
are giving Oshiroi
inspiration for her novel.
Wait, you're writing
about the brawls?
That's cool.
Well.
[SHIRAUME]
Sorry if I was rude but
I'm concerned about
Oshiroi's well-being.
Promise me you won't
push her too hard.
[YARIZUI] I have no intention
of pressuring anyone.
[SHIRAUME] Well,
in that case, she can stay.
[SHIRAUME] Before I go,
I have a message
from the student council.
[SATO] Are you a member?
[SHIRAUME] Would I deliver a
message for them if I wasn't?
[SATO] But we
just had the election.
I thought the results
weren't supposed
to be announced
until this weekend.
I assure you, I will be a
member of the student council.
I have ways of making
sure I always get what I want.
[SHIRAUME] Sato and
Oshiroi's applications for the
Half-Price Food Lover's
club are approved.
And now that you have the
minimum of three members,
your organization
will be added to
Karasuda High's
approved club list.
[YARIZUI] Thank you.
[SHIRAUME] Very well then,
if you'll please excuse me.
I need to get back to my
trash-collection duties.
Trash-collection?
Each day,
the student council
collects trash around campus.
[SHIRAUME]
Then we dispose of it in
the most efficient way possible.
We burn it.
[Sato cries out]
Don't forget about this stuff!
Oh, yeah!
[GIRLS]
One, two.
My uniform!
No!
[STUDENT COUNCIL GIRL 3A]
Hey, wait!
[YAMAHARA] C'mon.
Do you think I give a crap
about some dumbass
who jumped into an incinerator?
I heard that the
Ice Witch has been
lookin' for new Dogs,
and she found two.
They're freshmen students
Yo Sato and Hana Oshiroi.
They're both pretty weak
but they've got potential,
so I was thinkin' about asking
'em if they wanna join up with
us before they get too strong.
[DANDOU]
Here's a question for ya.
[YAMAHARA] Yeah, Coach?
[DANDOU]
What makes 'em so special?
[YAMAHARA] I dunno, but if
the Ice Witch has her eye
on two Dogs, there's
gotta be something.
[DANDOU] So they've got the
same ranking as you boys?
[YAMAHARA] Basically, yes,
but there's one defining
characteristic that
makes us different.
We're Hunting Dogs.
[YAMAHARA] We aren't scavengers,
we hunt, Coach Dandou.
[OSHIROI] You jumped head-first
into an incinerator and
you've only got five little
burns and three scratches.
Talk about amazing!
I know I'm lucky
I made it out alive but I
feel like I got
run over by a truck.
If you're
not feeling good,
maybe we should
skip the bento brawl.
Nah, I still wanna go.
I could use something to eat.
Hey, Sato. Do you
mind if I come with you?
You never
asked me before.
Sure, okay, we can go together.
"Go together"?
I'm so using that!
[YAMAHARA] Whassup,
Sato? Hey, Oshiroi.
[OSHIROI AND SATO] Coach Dandou
and the Hunting Dog Unit?
Isn't he the guy
with the perma-scowl
who also teaches Japanese?
[YAMAHARA] Yeah, but he
won't be joining us tonight.
He stopped by this
hole-in-the-wall place
called Hiro-chan's for some
miso ramen and fried rice.
[YAMAHARA] That's all
the poor guy can afford
on his measly teacher's salary.
Anyway,
my name's Yamahara.
I'm the captain of the
Kendo club and I'm also
the leader of the Hunting Dogs.
[SATO] Oh, yeah?
[OSHIROI] Hello.
It's hard to believe
you guys have
only been doin' this
for two weeks now. Crazy.
You're really good at it, too,
but I guess that's to be
expected when an awesome
brawler like the Ice Witch
is your teacher, huh?
Let me get straight
to the point.
How'd you like to join
the Hunting Dog Unit?
[YAMAHARA] I mean,
no pressure or anything.
We're not doing
too bad ourselves,
but we could use more people.
You don't have
to answer right away.
Why don't you just hang
out with us for a while
and see how it goes?
I can guarantee you a bento.
[SATO] Really?
[Sato's stomach makes noise]
Sure, we can
give it a try.
Yeah, sounds like fun!
Sweet!
Glad to have ya!
[YAMAHARA] You'll see eight
other guys wearing one of these.
They're your allies, the members
of the Hunting Dog Unit.
Okay.
[YAMAHARA] Whatever
you do, stick to the plan.
It sounds crazy but,
trust me, it'll work.
All you've gotta do
is follow our lead,
and you'll go home
with a warm bento tonight.
[SATO] Damn, he's fast!
[SATO] It's the
Hunting Dog Unit!
Okay, follow me!
[YAMAHARA] Let's go!
Wow, that was easy!
[OSHIROI] This is the first
time I've actually gotten one!
Can't you see they've
got bento in their hands?
Now back off, losers.
[KENDO CLUB A]
That was easier than last time!
[KENDO CLUB D] I didn't
expect it to go so well
with two newbs taggin' along!
[KENDO CLUB B] Yeah, no kiddin'!
[OSHIROI] Is something wrong?
No. No,
it's nothing.
[SATO AND OSHIROI]
Thank you for the food!
Wow, it's delicious, huh?
[YAMAHARA] What's up, Sato?
You're thinkin' about switching
teams now, aren't ya?
[SATO] Well, I dunno.
[OSHIROI] "Switching teams"?
It must be a pretty
tough decision for ya.
We may not be Wolves like
the Ice Witch but as you saw,
we can easily get
our hands on bento,
as long as we work together.
I'm sorry but
would ya mind if
I thought it over
a little longer?
Meet us tomorrow night.
We'll be at the same
place at the same time.
Until then,
hold on to the jersey.
It's a good fit on you.
[UCHIMOTO] Ben-To!
[KENDO CLUB A] I hate to say it
but I ain't so sure about
the newbs, Captain.
[KENDO CLUB F] Yeah, me too.
They don't seem like
they wanna join up with us.
[YAMAHARA] They may
not now but they will.
They're not gonna be
able to resist the urge of
getting their hands on
a bento every night.
The fact that they're
undecided means we've still
got a good chance of
winning 'em over.
[YARIZUI] Dandou and
the Hunting Dog Unit?
Why'd you go with those guys?
When we went to
the supermarket their leader
asked us if we wanted
to join up with them.
[YARIZUI] And?
[SATO] I told 'em
we'd think about it.
[SATO] They work
together in a way that
makes it super easy
to get bento but--
[OSHIROI ] This is the first
time I've ever gotten one!
[YARIZUI] Congratulations.
[SATO] I was really lookin'
forward to eating mine
but it didn't taste
all that great.
[YARIZUI]
Which one did you get?
The large Cheese Pork
Cutlet Curry Rice
bento from Tokiwa.
[YARIZUI] Come on, that's
one of their specialties.
There's no way it tasted bad.
They must've
missed the mark today.
It was just "meh."
[YARIZUI] Seriously?
[YARIZUI]
Oh, I get it now.
You get what?
[YARIZUI] Nothing.
Don't worry about it.
[SATO] Aw, c'mon,
don't leave me hangin'.
[YARIZUI] I remember
back when this club was
first started the
president once said.
"You may like bento now,
but wait until you've
tasted one that you've
earned at half-price."
[YARIZUI] Think about
that the next time you dig
into a bento and you'll
understand what I'm getting at.
[YARIZUI]
Thanks for the meal.
And just what do
you think you're doing?
You've already eaten.
[SATO] Just a little bite?
[YARIZUI] Not gonna happen.
[YARIZUI] Fine,
but you guys owe me.
Okay, ladies first.
Wait, you don't
want me eating
from your chopsticks,
do you?
I have no
problem with it.
What, are you worried that I'm
gonna give you
cooties or something?
No! I'm sure
you're cootie-free!
It's so yummy!
"Ah,"
That's tasty!
Thanks for lettin' me try it.
[OSHIROI] So what's up?
I can tell something's
bothering you.
[SATO] Listen, I was just
wondering if you'd wanna--
well, if you'd
wanna do it with me.
Wow. Uh.
I really don't know how to
respond to that, Sato.
That didn't come out right!
Uh.
I mean, it's not like I'm
not interested in you at all.
It's just--You're
a cool guy, but I want
my first time to be, well,
special, you know?
With someone I love.
But you can hold my
hand if you want to.
I meant do you wanna join
the Hunting Dog Unit with me?
Wait, what?
But I thought you asked
if I wanted to "do it"
with you--
Ow, quit doing that!
I've gotta
do something to
get your mind out of the gutter.
Is that really necessary?
[OSHIROI] I don't
want your hands to be
covered in germs
and oil from my hair!
[SATO] Got it!
You'd better let go of me!
[OSHIROI] Oh hey, welcome back!
[YARIZUI] I thought you were
gonna be out with Sato.
Nah, I decided not
to go, but I brought dinner.
Cool, then let's eat.
[SATO] You gonna make me go by
myself again tonight, Oshiroi?
Yeah, sorry.
Hey look, I wanna
show you something.
See this laurel wreath seal?
You won't believe how
we ended up with this one.
Our bus broke down in a
blizzard and we had to walk
three miles in the snow
to get to the supermarket.
[OSHIROI] Really?
[YARIZUI] When we finally
got there, ten Wolves
were crowded
around the last bento.
We weren't about to
let them take it from us,
so we challenged them
and a giant fight broke out.
It was such
a spectacular victory.
[OSHIROI] I can't
believe you beat me again.
[YARIZUI] Well, I can't
believe that this was
my twenty- third win in a row.
[SATO] There's no way
you're ever gonna beat her.
She's a pro,
just like I am at Virtua.
What's Virtua?
It's a game.
One of my all-time favorites.
See, it's a fighting game
called Virtua Fighter 2.
The stronger the enemy is,
the more fired up you get.
And you have to gain respect
from the other players.
Once you've won
them over, you'll get a
nickname and that
means you've really made it.
But only the
strongest get that far--
[OSHIROI] Wait for me!
I'm coming with you!
So I don't suppose
you're ready to
give me an answer
tonight, are ya?
You mean, whether
or not I'm gonna join you
and the Hunting Dog Unit?
[SATO] Well, I've
been thinking about it,
and I'll give you my
answer later on.
In my own way.
Aren't you gonna take one?
[YAMAHARA] What the
hell are you doing?
I'm giving you
my answer, Yamahara.
You make winning easy
but that's too boring.
The game's not rewarding
if there's no challenge.
What's the fun
in fighting for bento if
you can just walk
up and take one?
So here's a
little tip for ya.
Bentos taste better
when you earn them.
I'd rather have one I beat a
Wolf to get, than anything
you and your lackeys
could ever get me.
Oh yeah, I almost forgot
to return your jacket to ya.
Well, now
that that's over,
guess I'll be able to
enjoy my bento again!
Geez,
I completely forgot
that Hiro-chan's was
closed tonight.
We're the
Hunting Dogs, dammit!
As long as we work together,
we can be victorious
even if we're weak!
[SATO] Whether
there's two or twenty,
I'll take you Dogs down!
You did it, Sato!
I got one!
Sato!
Come back!
[DANDOU] Down, boy.
He's got a fire that you
and the other Dogs lack.
That kid has the eyes of a Wolf.
Sato.
Good to know.
[SATO] Be honest with me,
are you really cool with
being in the Half-Price
Food Lovers club?
Y'know Sato...
Ever since I was just a kid,
people have picked
on me for being a
little different.
I used to get bullied
a lot because I'm
a germaphobe
and a bit of an oddball.
But not anymore.
You and Yarizui make me feel
as though I really belong!
And--
I can't tell you how happy I
am that I met both of you!
And that's why, I swear,
I'm truly honored to be
one of the members of the
Half-Price Food Lovers' club.
I didn't know.
[OSHIROI] Come on,
let's go upstairs.
Don't just stand there, Sato.
Yarizui's waiting.
[YARIZUI] It looks like
you put up a good fight.
Lemme
ask you one thing.
What do the half-priced
bento mean to you?
Are they nothing more
than just left-over food?
[SATO] No, ma'am!
[BOTH] No, they're not!
They're so much more than that!
[YARIZUI] Keys to the clubroom.
Hold on to 'em.
[OSHIROI] Yes, ma'am!
[SATO] Yes, ma'am!
[ALL] Thanks for the meal!
[SATO] Finally!
A bento that tastes good!
[YARIZUI] You two owe me
a bite of yours, remember?
[SATO] What?
[YARIZUI] Okay, guys,
now we can call it even.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SHAGA] I challenge you, Sato.
[SATO] Huh?
What're you talkin' about?
And why're you fightin' me
with something so soft?
That didn't hurt at all.
It kinda felt good.
[SATO] No way.
Shaga?
The preview?
Do I have to?
The only reason
I came over here is
'cause I wanna play video games.
Let's finish
our match, Sato!
[SATO] Aw c'mon.
Can't it wait 'til next time?