[Sato cries out]
[WALLA: SHOPPERS]
[SATO VO] It was the
night of April sixth,
in the year twenty-eleven AD.
That's when...
I died.
[LITTLE BOY 1A] Hey Mama,
how come this guy isn't movin'?
I didn't miss it, did I?
The half-price bento.
[heels clapping on the ground]
[SATO] What happened?
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SATO] Looking back,
I can't help but
question my purpose in life.
I came into this world
fifteen years ago and
I've spent the last fourteen of
'em playing Sega games.
[SATO] I had a normal childhood.
I mean, I've had my share of
screw ups, like any other kid.
Like when I was little, I nearly
blew myself up at my dad's work,
and I didn't know
you had to pay to
get on the train until
a few years ago.
Other than that, my
life's been pretty boring.
Especially compared to
my pal Ishioka from junior high.
That guy's got enough
material for a primetime
TV show that'd
sell millions of DVDs.
[WALLA: SHOPPERS]
[GROCERY DUDE 1A] Aw, not again.
[stomach sound]
[SATO] I guess you can't
die on an empty stomach
or I'd be a goner.
[crowd murmuring]
[SATO] How did I get beat up at
the freakin' grocery store?
[Sato winces]
[Sato stomach growls]
Damn it.
Perfect.
Thank you.
Have a good evening, sir.
Yeah thanks, you too.
[SATO THINKS] I wonder
what she was she tryin' to say.
Was it....
"I love you"?
Wait, she loves me?
[YARIZUI] Hold me.
I'm just
a high school kid;
my feeble mind can't
handle that kinda fantasy!
[crowd reacts shocked]
[Oshiroi whimpers]
[SATO] Believe it or not,
all that happened on
my first day of school.
[SATO] It's the second
day of school and
I'm walking there from the ER.
Man, I can't remember
a thing from last night.
[OSHIROI] Um, Saito?
'scuse me, Saito?
[SATO] Who, me?
My name's actually Sato.
Yo Sato.
[OSHIROI] Oh my goodness,
how embarrassing!
Sorry about that!
Sato not Saito.
I'm just so glad you're okay.
I was awfully worried about
you after the craziness
that went down last night.
[OSHIROI] Wow!
Look at all your bruises!
I can't believe
you sprained your
left arm and your right ankle.
That takes talent!
Did you break any bones?
Maybe a few ribs?
[SATO] Thankfully
I wasn't hurt that bad.
[OSHIROI] That's good, I guess.
Although I was kinda hoping
you broke out of the hospital.
[SATO] The nurses were all like,
"You should be
hospitalized, just to be safe."
But when they called
my parents, my dad said,
"If the boy can walk,
then toss him out on his ass!"
and he hung up on them.
[SATO] So in other words,
"I ain't gonna pay the kid's
hospital fees!" Screw him.
I guess the nurses
let me stay overnight
because they
took pity on me.
You weren't admitted
but there's no
mistaking that you
were injured, right?
I'll try to hold back.
[SATO] Okay.
If only your injuries
were more visible,
then I'd have a better idea of
your current physical condition.
I remember going to the
supermarket last night
'cause I was really hungry and I
was hoping they might have some
half-price bento or somethin'
but I have no idea
what happened once I got there.
Are you telling me that you
don't remember anything at all?
Not even meeting me?
Uh.
You mean we've met before?
Huh.
[Oshiroi cries out
and then sobs]
Oh, crap!
What've I done?
What the hell is wrong
with you, Sato?
You just started high school and
you're already makin' girls cry?
Not cool, man!
So not cool!
What's not to like?
[Sato stammers]
[OSHIROI] If you don't
remember meeting me,
then that means you
must've lost your memory!
You're a lonely man who's
abandoned his tortured past!
My creative juices
are flowin' now, Saito!
Hey, if you were at
the supermarket last night,
then why dontcha be
a pal and fill me
in on the details
about what happened--
[OSHIROI] Oh, it was nothing!
Don't worry your
pretty little head about it!
[SATO] Hey.
She looks familiar.
[SATO] Let me see.
Where've I seen her before?
Yeah, that's it!
I remember now!
She was at the
supermarket, too,
and she kept staring at me and
trying to say something.
I think it's pretty obvious that
she's in love with me.
[SATO] Huh?
Where'd she go?
Is that for me?
Well, take it.
Don't just stand there, help me.
[SATO THINKS] The red tie
means she's a sophomore.
Sweet, an older woman.
[SATO] So, uh, looks
like all this trash
is nothin' but
empty bento boxes.
Yeah, today's the day
for plastic recycling pick up.
[SATO] I'm just surprised to see
so many of 'em, y'know?
[YARIZUI] That's because
our club forgot to take
out the trash before break,
and this is the first plastic
recycling pick up day we've
had since school started.
[SATO THINKS]
Geez, how many bento
do you go through in a day?
[SATO] Can't you
throw out a little at a time
so it doesn't pile up like this?
Don't you understand how the
waste system works in Japan?
Or have you been Americanized?
Plastic recycling is
only collected once a week.
Oh yeah,
believe me, I know.
[YARIZUI] Unfortunately,
I'm the only one in
my club who ever
takes the trash out.
[SATO] What kinda club are you
in anyway? You're the one who
was staring at me from outside
the store yesterday, aren't you?
[YARIZUI] Don't come to
the supermarket again.
[school bells chime]
[MALE STUDENT 1A] Alright,
who's ready to chow down?
[FEMALE STUDENT 1A] So,
what do you wanna do for lunch?
[SATO THINKS] I left these
fish cakes in the hospital's
fridge overnight, but now
they're all warm and gross.
Whatever, it's sustenance.
[SATO] I vaguely
remember buying them for
dinner last night,
but that's about all I've got.
Everything else is a
complete and total blank.
[SATO] Um, hello?
Who are you?
[SHIRAUME] My name is Shiraume.
[SATO] Hang on.
I know that name.
Oh yeah!
[SATO] Yesterday,
our homeroom teacher said,
"You need to elect a
class representative!"
which I thought was weird
'cause none of us really know
each other yet, but then--
[SHIRAUME] I'll do it.
[SATO] You volunteered
yourself and became
our class representative
on the spot.
[SHIRAUME] It's very
nice to meet you all.
Yeah, that's right.
You're Ume Shiraume!
[SHIRAUME] Indeed.
[SATO] No offense, but that's
kind of a weird name.
[SATO] When the teacher
wrote it on the board yesterday,
I thought, "That's Ume squared."
Ya mind
if I call you that?
[SHIRAUME] Yes, I mind.
Stop fooling around
or I'll get angry.
[SATO] You're not now?
[SHIRAUME] If you
know what's good for you,
you'll stay away
from Hana Oshiroi.
[SATO] Oshiroi?
[SHIRAUME] Don't play dumb.
I know you were out
with her yesterday
and you walked to school
together this morning.
[SATO] This morning?
Oh!
That girl with the glasses who's
been following me around?
Hey, if you're so "in-the-know,"
then what did we do yesterday?
[SHIRAUME] I warned you,
don't make me angry.
[SATO] Huh?
[Sato cries out]
[students ooh and ahh]
[MALE STUDENT 1B] Hey, did
I miss somethin', Uchimoto?
[Uchimoto giggles]
[school bells chime]
[SATO] If I'd known
Karasuda Private High School
had its own dorms,
I would've thought twice
about transferring here.
[SATO] Somehow
I just knew my old man
would make me move
in to be closer to school.
[SATO] The problem is
the dorm only serves breakfast,
so you're on your
own for lunch and dinner.
[SATO] I get that
they wanna teach
their students to
be independent,
self-sufficient adults, but
living on your own seriously
sucks when you don't know the
first thing about cooking.
[SATO] One month's allowance
is twenty-five-thousand yen,
and subtracting other expenses,
I'm left with a
daily food budget of--
If I eat light at lunch,
then I can stretch
my dinner budget to--
[YARIZUI] Don't come to
the supermarket again.
I'm afraid I don't
have much of a choice.
I knew you'd
be here Sai--.
I mean, Sato!
[OSHIROI] Don't mind me!
I'm just a fly on the wall!
I simply couldn't resist the
lure of burning, manly passion!
[SATO] Uh.
[OSHIROI] Wait!
Sorry to spook ya.
But go this way.
[YARIZUI] I told you
not to come here.
[SATO] Whoa!
Check it out!
They're half-price!
Tonight, I dine on bento!
[BENTO BRAWLER 1A]
No. It's you. The Witch.
[SATO THINKS]
What's he talking about?
[BENTO BRAWLER 1A]
You're the Ice Witch.
[SATO] But that's--
[SATO] Ben-To!
[SATO] That's right.
[SATO] It's all coming
back to me now.
[SATO] I was really
hungry last night,
so I went to the store
to pick up some dinner.
[OSHIROI] Oh my gosh!
I'm sorry!
[SATO] That's
where I met Oshiroi.
I, uh--I touched you
with my filthy hands!
[SATO] And then...
[SATO] It was game over.
[SATO] Aw, yeah!
Just a little higher!
All I need is one
little gust of wind!
Almost there.
Why the
heck am I all wet?
[ABURA] If ya got that much
energy, you must be fine.
Wait, where am I?
[ABURA] The Ho-Ki
Mart employee break room.
Would ya mind walkin' your
friend home when she wakes up?
[ABURA] The store's already
closed up for the night.
And the other guys
left a while ago.
[SATO] Um, sir?
[SATO] What were all of
those people doin' here?
Nothin' special.
They're just the kind of folks
who enjoy a little,
friendly competition.
Over bento?
[ABURA] Now I don't want to
be rude, but I get the feelin'
that you and
your friend here are
nothin' more than
a pair of lowly Dogs.
Dogs?
[ABURA] This place
is a regular store,
and I'm just your
run-of-the-mill
supermarket employee.
Most shoppers who come
in are picking up essentials,
but some of 'em come here
to test their skills in battle.
[ABURA] Sorry, kid, but you're
gonna have to step up your
game if you ever wanna get your
hands on a half-priced bento.
If you ask me, you're better off
buyin' one at full-price
like a good boy.
'Cause they'll
beat the shit outta you.
[SATO] C'mon, it's just
a silly bento, right?
[ABURA] You're lucky I'm
an employee 'cause
that's the only
thing stoppin' me.
A word of warning, kid.
If you call it
"a silly bento" in front
of the knights turned Wolves.
[ABURA] They'll kill you.
[ABURA] This store is a
hunting ground for the Witch.
[SATO] The Witch?
[ABURA] Yeah.
The Ice Witch.
[BENTO BRAWLER 1A]
You're the Ice Witch.
[ABURA] I feel bad that you
kids missed out on dinner,
so I left some protein bars
on the shelf for ya.
When your friend wakes up,
be sure to grab one
before you hit the road.
[ABURA] Oh, and here's
some tomato juice over
here if you'd rather
have that instead.
Later.
[guys react to power going out]
[FEMALE STUDENT 1D]
I heard the power went out
at the boys'
dorm last night.
Yeah, some idiot decided
to microwave a
protein bar with the wrapper
on it and killed the breaker.
[FEMALE STUDENT 1E] Seriously?
He left the wrapper on?
Wow, what a dumbass!
[SHIRAUME] I demand to know
your relation to Hana Oshiroi.
[SATO] Well, uh.
I'm not really sure
how to answer that.
We're fellow
supermarket casualties?
[SHIRAUME] You don't want
to make me angry, do you?
[SATO] I get the
feeling you already are.
[SATO]
[SHIRAUME] Yes.
[Sato grunts from
getting hit several times]]
[SHIRAUME] If you have no
intention of answering honestly,
I'll just have to ask
again later. 'Kay?
You must be crazy
to come here again tonight.
Maybe, but I guess
that makes you crazy, too.
[SATO] Are you ready for this?
[OSHIROI] Yeah, you bet!
[OSHIROI] Oh, how I love
the smell of hunky men!
[SATO THINKS]
I think I get it now.
Last time, the bento I wanted
just happened to be half-price.
It was nothin'
more than bad luck.
When I made
a move for it,
the whole supermarket
suddenly went insane.
I've never seen
anything like it.
It was like someone
ignited nitroglycerin.
[SATO] Hey!
[OSHIROI] Oh, I'm okay;
he just startled me is all.
I promise you I'm made
of stronger stuff than that!
[OSHIROI] I'm so sorry!
Your hands have
been sullied by my DNA!
[SATO] Geez, you really
are a germophobe, huh?
The Ice Witch is
here again tonight.
[SATO] Which one's your target?
[OSHIROI] I want the
"This'll Make You Sweat!
Feel the burn!
Super-Spicy Hamburger Bento!"
[SATO] Gotcha.
Then I'll go for the
"Stick with It, Natto Okra Rice
Bowl with Cheese Topping Bento."
[SATO] This is it!
[crazed shouts]
[SATO] Be careful!
Keep your head protected!
[SATO] Aw man,
I tried to tell ya--
[OSHIROI] They'll eat
you alive, Brunette!
[SATO] Calm down!
[SATO THINKS] Holy crap.
So these are the Wolves.
I never would've
imagined putting a half-price
sticker on a bento could turn
normal people into such savages.
[OSHIROI] Get up!
You gotta get back out
there and fight, Monk!
Damn, you're right!
He listened to me!
I've got
faith in you, Saito!
Don't die, but if
you do, don't you worry.
I'll weep for
you at your funeral!
[OSHIROI] Punch his lights
out! Look out behind you!
[SATO] Crap!
You should never
have come back here.
Hey, watch out!
[BENTO BRAWLER 1O] It's her!
[BENTO BRAWLER 1N]
It's the Ice Witch!
What? You have
gotta be kiddin' me!
She's the Ice Witch?
Then what was she
trying to say to me that night?
[YARIZUI] You idiot.
[OSHIROI] Yeah!
Go for it, Saito!
Bye.
Coming out tomorrow?
You know it.
[YARIZUI] Only the
strong dine on bento.
That is the rule
of this battlefield.
[SATO] But how'd you--?
[YARIZUI] If you want
to learn to survive here,
then meet me in
clubroom five-oh-one
tomorrow morning
at seven-thirty sharp.
[OSHIROI] Yeah, that
was pretty fun, wasn't it?
So, whaddya wanna do?
Go get something to eat?
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[SATO] Clubroom five-oh-one.
Well, this is it.
[YARIZUI] How's that feel?
[OSHIROI] Um, a little lower.
[YARIZUI] How about this?
[Oshiroi excitedly moans]
[OSHIROI] Oh, yes!
Yes! That's it right there!
[YARIZUI] Perfect timing.
Welcome to the Half-Priced
Food Lover's clubroom.
I'm the club president and its
only member, Sen Yarizui.
For now, I'll call you the
half-price-bento-seeking idiot.
Then I guess I should
call you the Ice Witch.
[YARIZUI] Whoa. How'd I get
stuck doing the preview?
It's not really my kinda thing.
Whatever.
[YARIZUI] Bento Brawls
aren't just a hobby,
they're a way of life.
You'll see.
Next time.