[SATO] Are you all right?
[YARIZUI] What time is it?
[SATO] It's almost six o'clock.
[YARIZUI] Seriously?
The God of Discounts
at Super Audrey
doesn't do his
markdowns until ten.
I've still got time to sleep.
I don't think it's a good
idea for you to go, Yarizui.
[YARIZUI] It'll be fine, just
give me another hour or two.
You know it's kinda funny.
That eel is
exactly what I need.
If I ate some I
wouldn't be so tired.
My body could use the nutrients,
and I'm getting hungry.
You would think that would
be enough to motivate me.
I have to go defeat Orthros, and
get my hands on the eel bento.
You rest.
And let me play
the hero for once.
[door opens and closes]
[opening song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
Man.
Maybe I should just take
a break for a little while.
Nothing's coming to me.
[OSHIROI] My laptop's
fixed and I get writer's block.
I'm just gonna have to
fight my way through it!
[sinister laughter]
It's about time
for us to leave.
Are you ready?
I'm just worried because
it's a Dog Day.
What if he's waiting for us?
[SAWAGI VP] It's been
three years since then.
Please don't worry, Sis.
Yeah, I know, but--but
I can't help myself.
So wait.
They moved because
of this Heracles guy?
[NIKAIDO] Yeah.
And according to my
sources, he's the one who
drove them out of
Yumehiro three years ago.
"Drove them out"?
What do you mean drove them out?
You've got to find a way
to save them somehow.
[SAWAGI PRES] It looks
like it's going to rain.
[SATO] I dunno.
[HERACLES] Aw c'mon,
what's the big deal?
You said you wanna
get an eel bento
for your sick friend
Yarizui, right?
Do you or don't you?
[SATO] Why're you doing this?
[HERACLES] Do you
honestly think I'd tell you?
Whatever.
[HERACLES] Give it
some thought, okay?
See ya.
I could cry. Because
to me you're like--
Go get me
an eel bento.
Please, Sato.
[SATO] If I don't stop thinking
about it, I'm gonna go crazy.
You okay? Or do you
just want to go home?
[SAWAGI PRES] I'll be alright.
I can do this, I know I can.
C'mon, let's go.
[BRUNETTE] Hey look.
It's the Pup.
[HERACLES] Figures he'd run.
[HERACLES]
So tell me somethin',
are you guys friends
with the Pervert?
I've always been told
history repeats itself.
I guess I'm about to
find out if that's true.
[rain begins to pour]
[HERACLES] That's just perfect.
Ugh, this freakin' downpour
came outta nowhere!
[SHAGA] Was that Sato?
[NIKAIDO] The Pervert?
[SHAGA] Hey!
Where the hell are you going?
Aw man.
What's gotten into that guy?
[SHAGA] Oh man,
I am totally soaked!
Is it just me or does
something feel off?
[NIKAIDO] They're here.
[SHAGA] Orthros!
See? I knew it
was a good idea
to go back home
and grab an umbrella.
[SAWAGI VP] Yeah, it
would've been had we not
gotten completely
drenched on our way there.
So, what's that smell?
And does it seem like it's a
little smoky in here to you?
[SAWAGI VP] If I had
to guess, I'd say it's
probably from all the
eel they're grilling.
The store's ventilation
system can't--
[SAWAGI PRES] Watch it, Kyo!
You should really
know better than to
stop walking when
somebody's right behind you--
It's him.
Hey there, ladies.
Long time no see.
I heard a rumor
that the two
of you had startled
bento brawling again.
At first I didn't believe it
'cause I thought you
lost your taste for half-price
food a while back.
But surprise, surprise,
here you are!
I'm only gonna
give you one warning, girls.
Get the hell outta
here and go back into
retirement or I'll be forced
to destroy you again.
So what's it gonna be?
Are you stayin' or goin'?
As you know, I'm
not opposed to beating
the crap outta lovely
ladies like you.
If I were you, I'd get
outta here while I still can.
This guy's tough.
Who is he anyway?
Heracles Combo.
It has to be.
[SATO] Heracles' Combo?
[HERACLES] That's me.
Well, kind of--I mean, that's
not my real name.
It's just my nom de guerre.
[SATO] So you're a Wolf, too?
[HERACLES] I have
something I need to ask you.
Nuh-uh.
We're going to stay.
[HERACLES] Are you sure?
Because I've already
talked to all the Wolves
here and they're on my side now.
I told 'em what happened
three years ago and they agreed.
[HERACLES] Things would go
smoother without you two here.
[SAWAGI PRES]
I don't understand.
Why're you doing
this to us again?
[HERACLES] You kiddin' me?
I thought I told
you this the last time.
You're too strong
for your own good.
[HERACLES] It disrupts
the food chain, y'know?
It's impossible for us
to have a fair brawl
as long as you two are around.
Just give up, Orthros.
There's no hope
for the two of you.
No!
We're not gonna give up on
the brawl because of you!
It's not over!
Somebody will come forward
and offer to fight alongside us.
You'll see!
I bet the Ice Witch
and the Pervert will help us!
[HERACLES]
The Pervert?
Oh yeah, you're talking
about that Yo Sato kid, huh?
I saw him outside
but he ran off.
[BENTO BRAWLER 5L] Seriously?
[BENTO BRAWLER 1J]
The Pervert ditched the brawl?
[BENTO BRAWLER 1P]
Do you guys think he
was scared of Heracles' Combo?
[SHAGA] Sato ran off?
But that's not like him.
[HERACLES] Okay, fine.
Go ahead and wait
if you want to.
[HERACLES]
Listen up...
If you wanna rid
yourselves of Orthros once
and for all, you're
gonna have to cooperate.
[HERACLES] What do
you do with a nail that
sticks out too far
to pound down?
Any guesses?
I'll tell ya.
You yank it out!
Like I did
three years ago.
Huh?
Oh. Hi.
How're you tonight?
I'm not too bad.
I can't believe
you came out again.
You really put
everything you got
into these bento brawls, huh?
Yeah, of course we do!
Maybe you'll be able
to beat us tonight.
Yeah.
I'm about to destroy
your world, ladies.
[SAWAGI VP] Sis.
What's going on?
Look, I've had just about
enough of you two.
You both win every single night.
Nobody else even
stands a chance,
and we always get stuck
with your leftovers.
[HERACLES]
I thought you'd eventually get
bored but I was wrong.
The thing is, we don't wanna
brawl with you anymore.
So how about you grab the bento
you want and get the hell out.
[HERACLES] What's the matter?
You girls came here for
half-price food, didn't you?
Go ahead.
[BENTO BRAWLER 12A]
Hurry up and take 'em already!
[BENTO BRAWLER 12B]
Yeah, we can't start the
brawl until you
twerps are gone.
[BENTO BRAWLER 12C] C'mon!
We ain't got all night!
Ya see?
This is more like it!
We can finally have a fair
fight without you around!
[HERACLES]
And don't come crawling back.
'Cause I won't
let that happen. 'Kay?
[NIKAIDO] So that's
how he drove 'em off.
[SHAGA] He's a
heartless bastard.
[doors open]
[GOD OF DISCOUNTS 12A]
All right! Who's ready
for half-priced bento?
If so, you'd better act fast
'cause it won't last long.
You're not gonna be able to find
this kinda quality any
cheaper, that's for sure!
[GOD OF DISCOUNTS 12A]
Only a few minutes left.
And then it's an all out war
for half-price eel bento!
[HERACLES]
What are you waiting for?
You can go ahead and
get your dinner, Orthros.
We'll wait right here.
You should know
the drill by now.
Hey, Sis? Can we
just take one and go?
Please?
[SAWAGI PRES] I guess
that's all we can do now.
I'm so sorry I keep dragging
you into trouble like this, Kyo.
I didn't mean to.
[SAWAGI VP] I know, Sis.
Hey you!
Way to go!
Y'know, for a second there,
I was worried you might
try to rebel, but I'm glad to
see you made the right choi--
[HERACLES] It's you.
Sato!
[ALL] Ben-To!
[OSHIROI] At the Super Bawdry,
where the stage is
set for a test of manly muscle,
Nick Kaido waited patiently.
[OSHIROI] Deep down he knew that
Saito, his partner in more ways
than one, was the only person
who could avert this crisis.
"He's our last hope.
If he can't stop this,
no one can!"
[OSHIROI] However,
it was obvious that
Saito wasn't his
usual manly self.
He was gasping for air and
soaked in ice-cold sweat.
[OSHIROI] As he turned
to look at the girls,
his gaze spoke clearer
than his words ever could.
[OSHIROI] "I'm sorry but
I can't pull myself
away from this
manly world for you!"
[OSHIROI] What's wrong with me?
Why can't I write
decent dialogue?
[SHAGA] Sato!
Do something!
[HERACLES] Don't ever
show your faces here again.
Got it, Orthros?
[GOD OF DISCOUNTS 12A]
And to top it all off,
the laurel wreath seal!
Laurel wreath seal?
[SAWAGI PRES] I want that bento.
Nothing else
can satisfy my hunger.
[SAWAGI VP]
What do you mean, Sis?
Life is too short
to live in fear.
I say we show Heracles'
Combo we're not afraid.
[SAWAGI PRES] If nothing else,
at least we can say we tried.
Yeah, okay.
Sorry if this seems
selfish to you.
I don't think you're
being selfish at all.
In fact, this is ultimately
what's best for the both of us.
We're Orthros, remember?
An unstoppable team.
It's us against the world.
We can do this, Kyo.
[HERACLES]
You want the laurel wreath?
Go ahead and take it.
[NIKAIDO] I can't believe
he's just offering it to them.
If only we had more time,
maybe I could've
convinced everybody
else to stand up to him.
[SATO] It smells so good.
Wait.
Huh?
After this,
you and I may never
be noble Wolves again.
I know.
Hey! You've gotta
go help them, Sato!
Fine. If you
won't, I will!
What?
[SATO] Be patient, Shaga.
Real wolves have a different
way of communicating.
We don't need words.
You'll see.
This is all we need!
[HERACLES] What the--?
[HERACLES] The Pervert!
[stomach growl]
[SHAGA] That's why he ran off,
to work up an appetite!
It didn't take me long to
figure out what I had to do.
See?
When one stomach growls,
the others take notice.
Luckily, we've got half-price
bento right in front of us.
And we've got the
instincts of a Wolf!
[SAWAGI PRES AND VP]
He did this for us?
Thank you, Pervert.
What the hell're you doing?
Stop fighting!
I thought you were with me; but
you're screwing up my plan!
Knock it off!
[SATO] 'Cause you're
nothin' more than a bully!
[BRUNETTE] The Pup's right,
why should we waste
our time with you?
I'm embarrassed
we went along
with your stupid plan
as long as we did!
You'll never be able
to truly appreciate the taste
of your half-price
bento if you force the
strongest wolves
out of the brawl.
[HERACLES] You bastards
think you're so smart.
It looks like you've left me
with no other choice.
I'll just have to beat
the ever-loving-crap
out of all of you!
You'd better get ready,
'cause you're about
to feel the wrath of
Heracles' Combo!
[HERACLES] You asked for it!
[SATO] Heads up,
Heracles' Combo!
[HERACLES] You've gotta yank
the nail that sticks out too far
or they're never gonna
learn their lesson!
I don't think so, pal.
There's another
way to fix that nail.
You get a bigger hammer!
What's that mean?
You get strong
enough to beat 'em!
Whatever.
There's no way!
Oh yeah?
Well, if there's anyone here who
can beat Orthros,
it's gotta be Sato!
[NIKAIDO] Right?
Don't mess with the Pervert!
He's a lot stronger
than you think!
All right, Perv,
you ready to do this?
[SATO AND NIKAIDO] Yeah!
You're goin' down, Orthros!
You think we should?
Well. Yeah! I do.
We came close to losing it all.
I'm so glad we didn't.
And it's all thanks to them!
[HERACLES] Damn you!
Okay, Orthros!
Get out there!
You guys want
the laurel wreath seal?
Then you have to fight for it!
[stomach growls]
[SATO] C'mon!
[SAWAGI PRES AND VP]
Excuse us, you're in the way.
[SAWAGI PRES] So hey, Kyo.
[SAWAGI VP] Yeah, Sis?
[SAWAGI PRES] Whaddya say
we show these awesome--
I mean, these pathetic brawlers
the power of Orthros?
[SAWAGI VP] I'm all for it!
[OSHIROI] I'm so hungry
I can't concentrate anymore.
I wonder if Sato's still here.
[NIKAIDO] It's all
or nothing now!
[SATO] There're only six left!
[SAWAGI PRES]
You can have the other five
but the laurel wreath
bento is all mine!
[SAWAGI VP] Calm down, Kyo!
[SHAGA] You ladies are gonna
have to fight a lot harder than
that or you're not getting
any half-price food!
[BRUNETTE] This is
delicious! For real!
This has to be the best eel
bento I've ever had in my life.
It's still so freakin' hot!
I don't know what
they do to their sauce
but it's the best.
Oh wow, this is yummy!
[BRUNETTE] And how is yours?
[SAWAGI VP AND PRES] Uh.
Well, it's pretty good, I guess.
[NIKAIDO] Orthros.
I was really impressed
by your tenacity.
Nice work tonight.
[SAWAGI PRES] Thanks.
We had a lot of fun brawling
with you guys tonight.
Let's do it again soon.
And next time, we'll win.
[BRUNETTE] Hey.
The Pup's not here,
where'd he go?
He left as soon as
the brawl ended;
said he needed to see the Ice
Witch about his punishment.
[SHAGA] Huh?
[GOATEE]
The Pervert's a masochist?
[MONK] I believe it.
[SAWAGI PRES] Nikaido, I'm kinda
surprised you're not with him.
I thought "the two dumb
dogs" were inseparable.
[NIKAIDO] Me and the Pervert?
No way!
Now stop calling us that!
Do you really think
she's gonna be upset, Sato?
You are such a moron.
[YARIZUI] Well?
How did it go?
[SATO] May I present
the laurel wreath seal.
[YARIZUI] I can't
believe you did it.
You never cease to amaze me.
[YARIZUI] Sato. In
your letter you said
sick people deserve
to be looked after.
What can I do to thank you?
I appreciate you
taking care of me.
How about you give
me half the bento?
Fine.
If that's what
you want, so be it.
Now.
You ready to dig in?
[SATO] You take the first bite.
But you're the one
who won the bento.
You should take the first bite.
But--
Go on, it's only fair.
But please give thanks first.
'Kay.
Thanks for the food.
[SATO] Whoa, it's so tender!
So how does it taste?
It's perfect.
And what makes you say that?
Well, it's hard to explain.
This eel is so incredibly
delicious that while the taste
of it is still lingering in
my mouth, I almost don't even
want to open it to speak for
fear I might lose the flavor.
It's that good?
I can't wait to try it!
Thanks for the food.
This is, by far, the best
eel I've ever tasted.
I don't know how you
got your hands on this
but I'm glad you did.
To be honest with you,
there was so much going
on tonight that I'm not sure
how it happened either.
But there's one thing I do know.
Be they weak or strong,
everybody deserves the
chance to brawl for bento.
I couldn't agree more.
No one should be
judged by their skill level.
That would make things boring.
I think the more brawlers
there are the more fun it is.
Don't you?
[SATO] Yep!
So to fill you in on
what happened tonight,
there are these two
Wolves called Orthros.
[closing song]
[girl singing in Japanese]
[YARIZUI] Let's go!
Hurry, guys!
[SATO] What's the rush?
[OSHIROI] Wait up, Yarizui!
My legs are shorter than yours!