Oh, my head...
Hangovers suck...
Ooh, cold!
Come check out Maid Café: Cozy.
Stop by and say hi!
Hope to see you at Maid Café: Cozy!
Man. My lower back hurts, too...
Running that new integration test
should be a straight-up blast today.
Dragons.
The most powerful of all beings.
An imaginary creature that has giant wings for
flight, possesses magical powers, and breathes fire.
Ah! Ta-dah!
Although, what do I know?
Having a good morning, Miss Kobayashi?
I don't know yet.
Do you mind allowing me in to your lovely home?
Oh. Sure, why the heck not?
So, you say we met yesterday,
and I offered to let you stay here.
With me. And you're for sure positive that's what I said?
Indeed!
This is weird.
Why am I not waking up from this dream?
Unless it's not a dream. There's no way.
So, um... Remind me where we met?
The mountains! We met in the mountains!
Mountains...
I remember mountains.
Okay, it's coming back.
A dragon?
Apparently, a hilarious dragon.
Oh, God...
So, wanna stay with me, "dragon"?
I'll never forget those wondrous words!
I can begin working as your
personal maid immediately if you want!
Oh, that's a big negative.
Huh?
I'm not like a dragon racist or anything.
I'm just not in the market right now to hire a maid.
But! You wouldn't have to pay me!
Yeah, no, that's not really...
Listen, I can be super helpful!
I can turn this area into a sea
of fire, or curse people to death!
No, no, no!
But, why maid instead of that?
Because you said a maid would work better for you!
I did, huh?
Yeah, does make sense...
I'm sorry, Tohru. I shouldn't have made that promise.
No one can change the impossible.
It's not, like, personal.
Are you certain...?
It's impossible?
Mm-hmm... Sorry.
I understand.
My apologies as well, for dropping in so suddenly.
Wanna stay with me, "dragon"?
Why won't this stupid guilt go away?
Maybe this dream... is really not a dream.
And if it's not, then...
I'm late?! Tohru!
Ah?
Can you fly?!
Ah!
Dragons are so fast!
Sorry, what did you say?
You're hella fast!
I could keep her.
Are you serious?!
So, now you can hear me?
I guess it wouldn't be the end of the
world to have someone around the house.
And if she's there...
This is murdering my lower back!
Okay. First, let's take a look at what you've decided is
the proper outfit for a maid and why that's totally wrong.
Great idea!
Here you go.
Huh...?
It's says Maid Café Cozy, see?
What is this?
I discovered some real life maids while on my way here.
Meaning we'll have to start from scratch.
First thing, as a housemaid... you clean.
Oh, I'm good at cleaning!
How's that?
No! It's all gone!
One moment!
You can bring it back?
Next! Laundry maid! Do laundry.
I can handle that, too!
I can produce a saliva that specifically removes stains.
Gross! No one wants to see that!
Next! Parlor maid! Greet people.
Easy thing for me!
Hi, I just need a signature for this delivery.
The foolish, inferior human is not welcome at this home!
Hey.
Oh, you're an exception of course, Miss Kobayashi!
Last one! Kitchen maid.
You cook.
Cooking is my specialty!
Try my very own roasted tail!
No, thanks.
Huh?
No way.
Wha...?!
Would you prefer it well-done instead?
That's not the problem.
Then I'm confident you'll enjoy it immensely!
I'm ethically against dragon tail.
Ah-hah! Seems you're a picky eater, Miss Kobayashi!
Dragon logic.
It grows back?!
Took a bit longer than usual
because I had to remove all the poison.
And it's poisonous?!
Hate to break it to you, but you don't know how to maid.
Then, I'll learn from the ground up!
Shall we start my education with
you telling me what you dislike?
What I dislike? I can't do hijiki or eggplant.
Interesting. I'll remember that.
Personally, I dislike eggs
when the yolks have been removed.
A while back, I had a friend named
Herensuge who was hit with one and killed.
That's a powerful egg.
Hold up. Why are you asking about dislikes?
Shouldn't you ask what I like?
No, that's bad luck.
Unfortunately, I've had far too many
friends slain by the very things they love most.
You know... liquor and women and jewels and such.
Sounds a lot like humans.
However, I can certainly let you know one thing I like!
It's you! I love you, Miss Kobayashi!
You gonna eat me?
No, not like that! Like sexually!
I'm not into women or dragons.
Yes, but I can't put a label on what I feel for you!
You saved me, and I'll use my
whole body to repay the favor!
Please use me to commute to work again tomorrow!
Thanks, but I got enough of that earlier. You're hard.
Gimme a chance, Miss Kobayashi!
I was raised to pay back all favors, even if they
were only owed to a foolish, inferior human being!
Call me crazy, but I sense bias.
Tohru, there is another reason I'd
rather not let you fly me to work.
Your back?
Well, that's half of it. The other half is...
You're too loud and too fast!
I think a dragon's place is in
the home holding down the fort!
Fort? What?
You're one of the stronger dragons, aren't you?
If you consider "starting Armageddon" strong.
I do, and please don't.
The world's dangerous enough without your help.
I'm just saying it would be a relief to
know you're here keeping the house safe for me.
Yes, I understand!
So consider it done!
So pretty.
Well, I'm off to the office.
If anybody calls, you can answer and take a message, yeah?
What's a "calls"?
Right, you're a dragon.
This is a phone.
When it goes "ring-ring," you pick it up like so.
Okay, got it.
They talk, then you talk.
They talk, then I talk!
Okay, take care.
Save travels!
Hold the fort?
Oh, is that what those people were doing?
I'll just ask Fafnir for help!
Kill them.
Kill all who try to steal your treasure.
Kill all who are suspect.
Curse them with death. Curse their generations to come.
He's always so helpful! All right!
Time to do my best to earn
Miss Kobayashi's love and praise!
Hmm?
The lady who lives here should be
gone all day, but let's make this fast.
We'll be in there before you can say "open."
Uh.
Save us!
Hmm?
There's a monster!
A monster?
We saw it, I swear!
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Hold the fort down all right?
I suppose, but it was lonely.
Ahh.
And I didn't even get to kill them.
Wait, what?
Hey, Kobayashi.
What is it, Takiya?
Want to grab some drinks tonight?
Sure, but, like, only one round.
So why me? There are plenty of other girls you could ask.
I don't want to go on a date.
I asked you 'cause you're like one of the guys.
Wow, how sweet.
What's with that girl staring us down?
Do you know her?
Uh...
Greetings, I'm Tohru Kobayashi. Miss Kobayashi's new maid.
Her new live-in maid. New violent live-in maid.
Hmm.
Yeah, it's my turn to take care of the "special" cousin.
I'm Makoto Takiya.
Kobayashi and I work together.
It's nice to meet you, Tohru.
And also you, Mister Takiya.
This man is clearly attempting to seduce Miss Kobayashi.
I shall not allow it!
Of course I can drink. You stultus.
Stultus?
Ah!
I love a good drink after work. It's the best!
Miss Kobayashi's the cutest!
I take it you won't be joining
us in our fight against sobriety?
I won't.
Got it.
I do not intend to share drinks with him.
What do I do about this silly man?
The laws are too strict in this world to do what I want.
I know!
I can flaunt how wonderfully close
Miss Kobayashi and I have become!
We're only secondary or tertiary
subcontractors, so why bother complaining?
Because I don't like how following their
directions consistently means we fail.
And the developers don't even
notice unless we point it out.
But making sure they don't have to notice their
faults is part of our job, so again, why complain?
I just think foisting their problems
on us is a pretty sucky thing to do.
I can't follow what they're saying at all.
Speak, Dragon, please.
Ah, I'm so sorry, Tohru.
We're not exactly including you in this discussion.
No, it's fine.
The topic's just so trite, I don't feel like joining in.
Okay...
We should be discussing the
ramifications of Ragnarok and Armageddon!
It doesn't matter, I've had enough!
Time to use force!
Let the jackals feed off you when you're dead!
Miss Kobayashi...?
Tohru...
Good maids don't talk that way! No threatening murder!
She's gone drunk!
On top of that, what's with your so-called maid uniform?
It's pretty disrespectful to maid-dom, if you ask me.
I mean, have a little self-respect. You look
like you're about to lose a cosplay contest.
Um, Mister Takiya?
Kobayashi! You're right, she's
just your basic cosplay maid!
It's cultural appropriation but without any culture!
Agreed! I can acknowledge the cuteness of
Gothic Lolita, but that's a specific fashion trend,
not cosplay! Why does it get so twisted?!
That's what I'm screaming!
Sure, Lolita and the maid fashion
do acknowledge each other, and
rightfully so, but they should be
careful not to blend into boring!
I think we're well beyond me just
being a part of this conversation, now.
Hey, Tohru!
We're giving you some high-level maid
conversation, so you better get in on this!
Maid talk!
Yes... I'm very sorry...
You know, Tohru, those horns are a nice,
if not confusing, touch to the cosplay.
Dragons have horns, and that is all I know about that.
Take it off.
Huh?
Take it off!
Huh...?
Come on! Gird your loins, sister! Cosplay me crazy!
Where's the shame in your role, maid?
I'm ashamed!
Give me more!
Show us what your "moe" is made of!
This is insane.
Bring more liquor.
Humans are terrifying!
And don't forget a good butler!
Sorry about that, Tohru.
Kobayashi and I go drinking because
we like to talk about all things maid.
As an undercover otaku, being able to share my
passions with someone else is kind of precious to me.
I understand that perfectly.
And I'm assuming this means
you won't mind a little surprise.
Heh.
We can just say I drank too much, too.
You really like Kobayashi, don't you?
Yes.
Since we're being so honest, you should know I hate you.
Okay, so humans beings all soil
their clothing with waste products?
Inferior species!
Miss Kobayashi's waste.
Oh, there's no more left...
I've said this before, so don't make me say
it again... Please stop licking my laundry.
'Kay. Then, I'll take care of it by licking you directly.
No licking me! Can we discuss the laundry?
Am I doing it wrong?
That's putting it mildly.
Tell me what you do beginning to end.
Well, first, I use my clairvoyance
to make certain your pockets are empty.
Good.
Then I separate them into piles by color,
and wash them in appropriate detergents.
Good.
Then I wash the delicates in my mouth.
No!
I told you I produce saliva that removes stains, yeah?
So gross! I told you nobody wants to see that!
Oh. Would licking make it better?
It's spit, not style!
Another thing. You can't wear the same
thing every day like you're in some anime.
You're going to have to change clothes, too.
But, these are my scales.
For real?
Yes. They're a part of me, so
I'd rather not take them off.
Oh. Makes sense.
Uh.
What's the matter?
It's just, uh...
I bought you some personal clothes.
Thank you very, very much!
Well, you're doing a lot for me, so
I wanted, um, to show appreciation.
Miss Kobayashi, would you like to have a sacrifice later?
How fun. Care for my fresh blood?
What am I, a demon?!
Heavens no! You're practically an angel!
But whatever you do, please do not start serving God.
Look, just try it on.
Ah!
Well?
It's tight.
What size bra do you wear?
A "D!" It stands for "dragon!"
At least you bothered to learn something. Gah.
Oh, crap, I gotta go.
All right, Tohru, use the Internet to study up
appropriate hygienic practices until I get home.
The inter-what?
Right. Dragon.
Oh!
You look it up like this.
I understand!
I'll see you later, then.
Safe travels!
The Internet!
Hmm, I still don't quite follow this.
I can just ask Fafnir to help me out again.
Kill them a...
Or maybe not Fafnir.
Quetzalcoatl is knowledgeable, so I'll try asking her.
Lucoa! Hey!
Tohru? It's been, like, forever.
So blah-blah-blah and yadda-yadda?
Mm-hmm...
Yeah...
This doesn't sound like a problem of clean or dirty.
Huh?
Well, you remember Nidhogg, don't you?
The one who gnawed on that tree's roots?
The world's tree, yes.
No matter how much Nidhogg's poisonous fangs
pollute Yggdrasill, the goddesses purify it,
so the tree stays clean. However...
Yes?
What do you figure happens to the spots he gnaws?
Ah...
As I recall, he leaves energy behind.
Something like a curse?
Yep, that's it.
This Miss Kobayashi you speak of is worried about that.
Of course! Thank you very much!
Tohru.
Are you enjoying living amongst the humans?
I am!
At this rate, Miss Kobayashi's
laundry is never going to get dry.
I know!
Great work, Tohru.
Really starting to doubt my maid teaching skills.
What just happened?
I know that breath.
I know it well.
Surely there's nothing wrong with inhaling the scent?
I don't imagine you need sleep?
Nope. But I wanna sleep with you,
so I think I'm gonna go to bed anyway!
Whatever, do what you want.
I have a feeling you don't mean that!
Well, nighty-night.
Yes, good night.
It's cramped.
Do you want me to go?
Nah, it's fine.
You okay?
It was a fight. In another world.
I was run through by a sword.
I bet that hurt.
Yes, quite a lot.
And does it still hurt?
No. It doesn't hurt now.
That's good, then.
Ah.
Sweet dreams.
Welcome back home, Miss Kobayashi!
I said welcome home.
Welcome back, girl!
So, what are you working on, Tohru?
Miss Kobayashi! Tell me what you like this time!
Maids.
You mean me, then?
No, not you.
What else?
I dunno, peace.
So you're saying I'm enough for you?
Nope. I never said that.