Christmas, huh?
I do hate the idea of celebrating
the birth of You-Know-Who's son,
but I gotta say, it sounds like a good time.
Tohru, hey!
Hey back!
Oh, no!
What happened to you?
Unfortunately, I was practicing for the local
retirement home's annual Christmas Eve show,
but I ended up injuring myself.
You must feel so weak and flimsy.
Oh, hey!
Tohru, do you think you might be
willing to put on the show in my stead?
The residents in the home were looking forward
to the event, so I feel like I'm letting them down.
Put on a show?
Are you serious?
Yes, of course.
No one could represent our
shopping district better than you!
Okay, we'll do it!
And don't worry, it'll be super!
And so I'm totally gonna do it!
Are you sure?
Sure, I'm sure!
I'd like to help out, too, but I can't.
I have stupid work.
That's all right, Miss Kobayashi.
You just stay focused on your job,
and I'll take care of everything.
Whatever. If you say so.
It'll be easy.
All I gotta do is ask my reliable
and free friends to help me out!
Ready, everyone?
Let's put on a show!
Yeah!
Um. Yeah.
Wait a second!
Jeez, what is it?
Have I been lied to? Because I was told I could
eat as much candy as I wanted if I came here.
I even made room in my schedule even though
it's one of the busiest times of the year!
Miss Kobayashi told me the truth about you, Elma.
You're completely useless at work.
So much so that they've even announced they
didn't need you to be in their way right now.
Ah... It doesn't make any sense!
Now I can actually type with my fingers!
What else can I do when I can't
afford to interfere with this world?
Believe me, you're already interfering plenty.
Question.
Why isn't Kanna's mom doing this?
Unlike Elma, Miss Kobayashi is busy with her work, so,
it's up to us to take care of this on our own!
What do ya say?
Boring.
I heard something important was happening.
Turns out it was just something pathetic instead.
Oh, come on, Fafnir!
Let's keep an eye on how it goes.
Well, then.
What exactly do you want us to do for this show?
I think, to start off with, it should probably be
something the elderly would enjoy watching.
That works for me. Any other ideas?
I know!
An eating contest!
No. You just wanna stuff your face.
How 'bout a race?
That might kill them.
We should play a VR FPS, FFA, AKA frag fest.
I'm sorry, could you use words?
But all of these ideas require
the audience to participate.
You can't judge us when you
haven't actually proposed anything!
Do the two of you have any suggestions?
I'm okay with whatever.
Okay, so, what if we put on a play?
Wait, a play?
Is that where humans pretend to be different humans
on a globe stage that's not a globe?
Globe stage that's what?
A play, huh?
That's perfect!
Let's put on a play!
Fine.
We will put on a play, but what
do you think we should put on?
Since it's Christmas time, why not The Little Match Girl?
Ooh, that sounds funny. Is it funny?
Um, no.
It's about this poor little girl selling
matchsticks on a very cold winter's night.
Sadly, no one will buy any matches from her.
So, in order to warm her chilled body,
she lights one of the matches.
Then, in the flame, she sees a
warm stove and lots of delicious food.
She lights match after match,
and eventually, her beloved and yet
very much dead grandmother appears to her.
The little girl continues lighting her matches
to keep her grandmother from disappearing,
until finally, the grandmother
gently hugs the little girl.
Then the little girl ascends to Heaven,
embraced in her grandmother's warmth and love.
It's kind of a sad story, and gosh, it gets me every time.
Yeah, it's pretty famous.
Oh.
So, what happens after the girl ascends to Heaven?
Does she sell her matchsticks?
Idiot.
The girl ascends to Heaven because she's dead.
Wow.
That woman strangled her own granddaughter.
Die!
No, that's not it either.
You know a lot, Saikawa. It's so cool.
Yeah, I guess.
It's no big deal.
I'm good with putting on The
Little Match Girl if you guys are!
Yeah!
Sure hope we don't blow it.
Fafnir will obviously be directing.
Keep in mind, Fafnir will not
stand for any sophomoric performances.
Fafnir is the absolute authority.
Challenge him and you will suffer.
Also, keep in mind Fafnir's only
the director because he can't act.
Now, come on nepotism!
Before anything, Fafnir needs
to cast the lead of this play.
He wants each of you to audition
for the role of Little Match Girl.
Yay! I can go first!
Tohru, auditioning for Little Match Girl.
Just get started.
Do not disappoint Fafnir.
Matchstick.
Oh, please, won't anyone buy a match?
Boring. Next.
What? Already?
I'll give you one more shot.
This time, see those heartless humans
ignoring you like the trash you are.
Feel it.
Then, allow the lines to flow naturally.
Feel it, huh?
Why, you foolish, inferior humans!
How dare you ignore me to suffer like this?
I'll make you pay for...
Fail. Next.
...with your dead!
Hello, my name is Elma, and I'm unrepresented.
Matches?
Do you need any matches?
I don't.
Please, sir! Please at least hear me out!
I can't go back to the office until I've sold them all.
What are you doing?
The salesmen that come to our company
always put on a performance like that.
Sucks for them.
Next.
Good afternoon!
I'm Riko Saikawa.
Thank you for your time.
I... Uh...
Oh, god, why?
I'm so sorry!
To be honest, none of you are any good.
To be extra honest, your directing
style is way too sadistic for us.
Ooh, me!
Yeah, you what?
Let me direct.
I can be nice and firm!
And I'll make Shouta the lead.
What are you even talking about?
Shouta's a boy, not a little girl.
Well, you just leave that to me.
Shouta, baby, come here.
He looks just like a girl!
So cute.
Yeah, I'll buy it.
I dunno.
He's not as cute as Kanna.
Wha...
"Wha"?
What are you all planning to achieve by embarrassing meee?
Well, that was to be expected.
C'mon, cheer up, sweetie.
What should we do, now?
I can be the director.
I'll at least be better than those two.
That's true.
Any thoughts on who we should make our lead?
Matches.
Please buy some matches.
Perfect!
Hey, guys, I'm home.
Matches.
Do you wanna buy any matches, please?
Mind filling me in?
We decided to perform The Little Match
Girl for our show at the retirement home.
Kanna has been cast as the title character.
Oh, I see.
Congratulations, Kanna!
Mm-hm. I'm excited.
I promise to come see you.
You sure you'll be okay?
Of course we will!
There's no way a play can take down a dragon.
Right.
Do you want to buy any matches, please?
She's at her most dangerous when she gets like this.
If you say so.
Match?
I'm gonna go take a bath.
'Kay!
Coming, phone.
Hello, Kobayashi residence.
It's me.
I thought about the script some on my own.
You're still not gonna be the
director, so if it's that, let it go.
Otherwise, what did you come up with?
If we stick to the original play,
it won't match the current era.
So, I decided to make the
little match girl into a magical...
All right then, time to prepare Miss Kobayashi's dinner.
Do you want to buy any matches, please?
Lady Tohru, is there a chimney in this house at all?
Is there a chimney?
No, why do you ask?
Because Saikawa told me that Santa visits
your house by coming down the chimney.
Oh, yeah, you mean that old man who's covered in blood?
Do you think Santa will still try to visit us?
Yes!
What the crap?
What are you doing?!
No, no!
How many times do I have to tell you?
No, where do you think you're going?
Tohru! Why would a rando use Kobayashi
as reason to refuse to buy matches?
Yeah, well, why would I be in a hurry
if I wasn't doing something for her?
Not my problem!
Lucoa! The grandmother would not try to
warm the girl up while practically nude.
Why not?
It's much warmer this way.
Fafnir, you're completely out of line.
A human father would never
call his daughter a "mere human."
Focus!
Why is accepting this script such an ordeal?
Well, I don't think it translates
that well, culturally speaking.
Not to mention it's slow and
repetitive and might bore the audience.
True, and we don't want that to happen.
Then why don't we try changing things up just a bit?
What are you suggesting we do?
Nothing too extreme.
I mean, I think at the very
least, we should make it more fun.
That sounds good to me!
Why don't we mix other myths in
with it, like the Kasa Jizou story!
Like we have the old man selling hats next to the girl.
Or we could follow the script.
I like it.
The main character should be a magical girl.
She can obtain power to burn this corrupt world,
burn it to ash.
Now there's nothing from the original left.
You know, I've heard 47 Ronin is popular with the elderly.
Oh, yes, the one about humans and their quest for revenge.
I can appreciate that.
Are there any dragons?
We might as well have some while we're at it, right?
Hey, Grandma!
Stop making it sexy!
Narrator, stop grinning like an idiot!
Kanna.
From what I've heard, this Santa guy
won't be coming by for a little while longer.
Does Santa know where we are?
Will he really come?
I guess we'll have to wait and see.
I'm exhausted.
What the crap?
Merry Christmas!
Still have some cake left!
Are we too late?
No, we're good.
It's just about to start.
All right, now the performance of The Little Match Girl
brought to you by the wonderful
Oborozuka Shopping District.
Please enjoy the show.
The City.
It was terribly cold that night.
A light shone upon the street corner.
Standing in that light was a girl selling matches.
Matches.
Do you want to buy any matches?
Unfortunately, no one wanted to buy her matches.
I can't sell any.
Umm.
Excuse me, young girl.
Would you like to buy some hats?
Before her appeared an old man selling very strong hats.
I'm an old man, and my old wife
made these hats for me to sell.
Oh, they're very strong.
I do not have any money.
Are you all right?
I'm cold.
That must be difficult.
Here, you can burn one of these to get warm!
Burn the hat?
Odd choice since his wife made it!
They're actually setting it on fire!
Then something unexpected happened.
A strange smoke appeared, and with it, a suspicious man.
Look, pathetic humans.
Who are you, sir?
What do you want?
You have been chosen.
You will be a magical girl with a duty to bear.
I did not see that one coming.
I grant unto you the power to
correct and punish this corrupt world!
Okay!
That was quick!
Very good.
Let us go.
Wait! Me, too!
I want to be...
...a magical girl!
Why do you wish to be a magical girl?
So I can use my power to commit many nefarious deeds.
I need the money, you see.
My wife is very poor and dying from a terrible sickness!
Why wouldn't he just heal her with his magical power?
You would dare voice your desires
like that without any shame, old man?
Acceptable.
You shall be a magical girl, too.
Oh. This is embarrassing.
But, unfortunately,
I only have one staff that
will allow you to use your powers.
You will fight, and the survivor shall have the staff.
Now!
No, you must not fight!
I am a magic fairy.
Do not let yourselves be fooled
by that suspicious man's offer.
I shall not allow you to toy with the hearts of others.
Leave this to me and go, little girl and old man girl!
No, magic fairy, we cannot just leave you here.
That's right!
You are so kind.
Our time together was very enjoyable.
I shall never forget you two!
It was seconds.
No way.
Do you know what we should do now?
A magical girl's role is to cleanse
corruption from this world, right?
I'm on it!
Where are all the bad and rotten people?
Incredibly, the spell cast by the young girl
struck a devastating blow to a nearby mansion.
Let's go look over there.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Are you the two responsible
for setting this place on fire?
No, what? Who would do such a mean thing?
So guilty.
I'm very sorry. I meant nothing ill by it.
It's cool. Don't worry.
I am Kuranosuke Oishi.
Thanks to this fire, I can
easily sneak into the Kira mansion,
so you have my utmost gratitude.
What are you doing here?
I've come to finally avenge my lord and claim
the head of Kira Kouzuke No Suke Yoshinaka!
Now it's the 47 Ronin?
Avenging your lord? Hilarious!
Prepare yourself, Kira!
If you'd forfeit your life, come!
She did not just do that!
That's the source of the corruption.
And the enemy of all magical girls!
No!
No one can beat me in this: My final and ultimate form.
I'll turn you into dust!
They have to stop before they lose control!
That's amazing.
This must be that CGI!
Ya darn right I'm spry!
No, CGI.
All right.
Then, I'll have to get serious, too!
I dare you!
What an incredible show!
Kobayashi!
So, what did you think?
We were amazing, right?
Yes, you were.
I'm proud that you did it all on your own, too.
Good job, Tohru.
Thank you!
Does anybody wanna join me for an after party?
Let's do it!
We can take this appreciation cake they gave us!
Elma.
You just wanna stuff your face again.
What? That is not at all true.
Cheers!
Ouchie.
Where is everyone?
They just left to head to their homes.
Apparently, they're each having
their own, individual parties, too.
What about Kanna?
She escorted Miss Saikawa home.
Would you like a bath?
Or are you too tired to mess with that tonight?
Well.
Since it's Christmas, I have an idea.
It's beautiful!
You sure you're not cold?
No, I'm great!
This is unusual.
You've never asked me to see the view at night.
That's weird.
Oh.
I almost forgot!
Here!
What?
Is this Christmas gift for me?
Yes! I got you some medicine
that works well for lower back pain.
For real? That's so sweet!
It's a valuable item in the other world!
You grind it down and apply it to your achy areas.
It works exquisitely!
Yeah.
Right.
Ya know, I was worried about you all day today.
What for?
What do you mean?
To be honest, I was super
anxious while watching your play.
Kept worrying if and when I should jump in to stop you.
But then, I realized everyone loved it.
You really did a nice job.
Thanks!
It's a White Christmas.
Here, I sorta got a Christmas present for you, too!
Uh? What is it?
Merry Christmas, Tohru.
Enjoy!
Miss Kobayashi!
Tohru, slow down! I'll fall!
I can't!
I suck at this!
Fafnir, that was quite the excellent performance!
"Look, pathetic humans."
Stop it.
"Huh? Why do you wish to be a magical girl?"
Don't mock me.
"Acceptable.
You shall be a magical girl, too."
I'll kill you all!