Miss Kobayashi! Kanna!
Breakfast is ready!
Your miso soup is killer today.
Thank you, I'm glad you like it!
I decided to try something different
and only use ingredients from this world.
Hmph.
We'll see you later.
Okay.
Be sure to watch out for those cars!
Mm-hmm.
Remember, Kanna, if a car hits
you, you'll smash it to bits.
I know.
Perfect! Miss Kobayashi didn't get angry or
chastise me about anything I did this morning!
Success, Tohru! Success!
I feel like my maid skills are definitely improving!
Hey, that could mean I'm finally
getting used to this world. Yay!
I don't know what's going on with you,
but you've been a lot happier lately.
What? I have?
Yeah, it's not like you were sad, but you
were a bit more stoic. Well, a lot more stoic.
I dunno, you just seem a lot
more open, if that makes sense.
See you later!
It's been, what? Two months now since she showed up?
Two months, and I have no idea
what I was like before then.
The secret to this dish is to marinate it in honey.
I should try that.
Yeah, maybe then, Miss Kobayashi
will give my tail meat a shot.
Our poll reveals how women really want
to be treated by their significant other!
Being knocked back on a wall is number one?!
Okay. So they're like birds. They pursue love with sound.
Pursue... Love...
Miss Kobayashi...
Tohru.
And now for the evening news. Early this
morning, a fire broke out in Tatsumicho Nishiku.
Kobayashi.
Hmm?
Y'know, I hate asking, but would
you mind helping me out with this?
Sure, whatcha got?
Whoa. Looks like I'm not the
only one who takes on too much.
I've been wanting to see what Miss Kobayashi is
like at work since I first found out she had a job!
One of my 48 maid skills: Perception blocking.
Now I can walk around without anyone noticing.
Ah! There she is!
Well, looks like I don't have any other choice.
Yeah, thanks. You, too.
Uh-oh, that didn't look very good.
Takiya?
Yeah, no. Remember that project Yamashita was working on?
Well, there's a big problem with it.
And if it's not fixed today, he'll basically be screwed.
Ah...
Sorry.
So, as of now, I've gotta prioritize that.
Meaning I can't help you.
At least, not at until that's fixed. I'm sorry.
Why're you apologizing?
I totally get it. No worries.
Hmph.
Hey. We need to go drinking again.
Hey, can you help me here?
Sure thing. Gimme a minute though.
This schedule sucks. I mean it's just impossible.
There's gotta be a way to push it back.
Gotcha. But this still needs to be reevaluated.
Humans may gather together, help each
other, and accomplish a lot of things,
but their civilization could
easily be destroyed by dragons.
Bottom line, I still think dragons are way better.
Kobayashi!
Come on, you've gotta be done by now.
No. Not yet.
Y... What are you doing?! Are you completely useless?!
Did you forget that part when I
told you to finish it "immediately"?!
Who's this jerk?!
Big shock. The Chief is yet again
pushing his work off onto Kobayashi.
It's nuts because his project isn't even that crucial.
Listen, honey...
You better quit screwing around
and finish this thing fast, got me?!
Understood, sir.
Grr! Christ...
Pfft!
Cheese it, guys!
Hmph! Serves him right.
That oughta cheer up Miss Kobayashi.
Uh! I thought I was blocking perception.
No, there's no way anyone knows I'm here.
Miss Kobayashi sure works hard.
And that's on top of everyone
asking for her help all the time.
Miss Kobayashi is just... She's just the best!
Kobayashi!
Hmm?
You better be close to done! Why haven't
you given me any work progress updates?!
This jerk again?
Yeah, about that. I've had a
lot of other things to do, so...
"Other things"?! You follow my orders first!
I understand, but your work's not my priority.
Don't back talk me!
Focus! And fix that attitude now!
Yes, sir.
Christ! Completely useless!
Ow! C'mo... Ow!
Who is doing that...?
Ah!
Is that karma? Because it looks like karma.
Why me...?
Thanks for your help today!
No problem! See you tomorrow.
I'm heading out too.
All right.
I should probably get home before Miss Kobayashi does.
Tohru.
You're here, right?
You really were!
Uh. Yes, but how did you know?
Uh. I guess I just kinda had a feeling.
But whatever.
I bet my job was a lot more
boring than you expected it to be.
No, it wasn't boring at all!
I wanted to learn more. More about you, I mean.
And I did.
Hmph.
Cool.
Ready to go home?
Yes!
I don't know what's going on with you,
but you've been a lot happier lately.
I wonder what I was like before.
Hmph.
I've already forgotten.
I heard someone got the chief
canned for abusing his power.
Apparently, the director got an
anonymous recording proving it.
Whoa, who do you think turned him in?
Okay, I'd like everyone to find a friend.
When you're paired up, draw a picture of your partner.
Okay.
Ah! Hi, Kanna.
Do you wanna draw me, maybe, please?
Hmm.
You're my friend.
Asparagus, watercress, and potatoes!
Hooray for vegetables that are in season!
And since they were cheaper than I figured,
I can pick up some snacks for Kanna. Huh?
Fafnir?
I'm home from shopping!
Welcome back.
That was a surprise!
I never expected you to be standing there.
Oh, that's for you.
So what's going on?
Hmph.
I've made the decision to live in this world for a while.
What? Seriously?
To be honest, I don't recommend it for you at all.
You know you're gonna have to live with humans.
Yes, I know that. But if you can do it, then so can I.
I guess that's true.
Ooh, maybe you could stay...
Somewhere that's not here.
Do you have any thoughts on where you want to live?
I imagine a nearby mountain should suffice.
And now for the news.
Last night, accounts of a monster spotted in
the mountains were called into emergency services.
Police were dispatched to investigate a
creature that's reportedly 20 meters tall.
What? Don't judge me.
Why should I be forced to hide who
I am in order to appease the humans?
Perhaps... I should simply destroy them.
Oh, stop being so dramatic.
If you want to live around humans,
you'll have to fit in. That's just the way it is.
I know, restraint sucks.
Hey! You know what?
I don't mind helping you search for a new place to live!
Uh. You sure you want to get involved with that Tohru?
Yes! Don't worry I'll be fine.
I can do this! You in, Fafnir?
Hmph.
It certainly won't hurt to see what you can do.
Just the other day, I watched Miss Kobayashi
move out, so I've got the process down.
Oh?
First you create a family registration.
Then a proof of citizenship, a
bank account, and a personal seal.
You gather all that stuff and show them to a realtor.
I don't have those things.
Nope! So, I created them all for you!
Hold on.
Holding!
Huh? Is that me?
Yes. Your dragon form looked like a
Takeshi Ooyama to me, so I went with it!
You're too much like them.
Huh?
You have grown far too close to these humans, Tohru.
What happens when you return to your world?
Will you kill them? Will you even be able to anymore?
Doesn't matter, I don't intend to return to my world.
Why would I? This is clearly where I belong!
Eventually, that human you've
become so attached to will die.
What then?
Look, I promise you I'm fine.
I know the more I treasure being here and these moments,
the sadder I'll be when the time comes.
But I'll embrace it.
I never want to confuse those feelings with regret.
Because she's worth it!
Come on... green means go.
And you genuinely believe these creatures
are worth such high praise, do you?
Yes, I do.
Miss Kobayashi is one of them.
Hmph.
What's the deal, Fafnir? Why so worried about me?
I was merely curious about what humans
are like in this world, no more, no less.
Well, if it isn't Miss Kobayashi's maid.
That's me! Can you help us?
So. What's your budget?
You mean payment?
Heh. Sorry, but we take money, not gold.
That was a bust, huh?
This isn't a problem. I can just go steal a...
Nope. No, you can not.
I cannot fathom no currency exchange.
This is such a limited world.
Yeah, about that...
It seems, I don't know, are you sure it isn't best for you
to live in your own world and just come, like, to visit?
It's gotta be hard to live here
without a human you get along with.
Hmm?
Except that there is a human you get along with, Fafnir!
Yes, who is it?
Hey, Tohru!
Oh! What's up, Fafnir? Good to see you.
Kinda weird that you know where I live, though.
I asked Miss Kobayashi.
Mister Takiya?
How can I help you?
It's, um, Fafnir has no home right now.
Would you mind if he stayed with you, please?
You want Fafnir to live here?
Yes. That okay?
Sure, it's totally fine.
What?! You... You mean it?
Well, it'll be cramped, but I don't mind if you don't.
Are you sure, like, sure?
I know I'm one to talk, but
this guy's a very dangerous dragon!
Hmm?
The last time we met...
You like that game?
Yes, but I'm curious... are there more?
Why don't you come on in?
Tell me about these "games."
You got it!
Something makes me think maybe Fafnir's decision
to stay here had precisely nothing to do with me.
Correct.
Let's conduct the experiment according
to the chart located in your textbook.
Okay.
I forgot to bring my book. Share with me?
Ah! Yes. Well, if I have to.
Hmm.
Now please give me the spoon.
Physical strength is not necessary.
I'm going to bend it using my mind.
That spoon was not bent with physical strength.
I saw it!
And as far as I can tell, he didn't use magic.
Like this, right?
I feel like it was something like this.
Not that.
Tohru!
Guys... You destroyed them.
Yeah... We're sorry about that...
What were you trying to do?
Over there. Look there. Look there.
Huh? Oh, right.
Of course you were.
I guess you've never heard of psychic powers before.
Psychic powers?!
So are you telling me that
humans really do have hidden powers?
I told you Miss Kobayashi was no ordinary human!
She's a Kobayashi God!
Yes, she is!
Listen up, dragons. This is a trick.
Anyone can do magic tricks... if they learn.
Sorry? Anyone?
I've heard of this before.
There's a "should be forgettable"
movie that talks about it.
About how humans only use approximately
ten percent of their brain capacity.
Basically, if humans weren't so lazy,
they would be able to have super powers.
All they have to do is try.
Such potential killed by inherent laziness.
I can't forgive that! Damn humans!
I have a strong feeling I don't
like what you're thinking right now.
Lady Tohru. I found this book on Kobayashi's shelf.
Well done, Kanna!
Oh, I bought that thing forever ago.
According to these instructions, there's a
move that allows power to enter your hand.
It's fictional though, not real.
Ah! That's not true!
This book is clearly instructional!
I'm gonna train with it!
Your susceptibility could feed an entire cult.
I know, right? Come with me!
Why not? I got nothing else going on.
Wait, let me fix your spoons real quick.
I don't get this. You don't need psychic powers.
That's great. Very cliché.
May the surrounding energy tell me if
I'll actually learn anything this way.
Mm?
It doesn't matter if she can do it, so why?
Empty the mind. Right now, I have no desires.
Kobayashi, I'm hungry.
For you are weak!
Ah...
Hey!
I want some, too!
Here.
Ah...
A star!
Incorrect.
Miss Kobayashi! Miss Kobayashi!
Uh... Miss Kobayashi?
Nope. Pretty sure that's your horn.
Hyah! Hyah!
Miss Kobayashi, please look!
Presenting...
Compilation Bear Slayer!
What does she want out of this?
Hup... Chop, chop, chop...
Come on, no fair!
Listen, Tohru.
Hmm?
You can do so many things humans can't,
so why is this such a big
deal? Maybe you should let it go.
I will not!
I will never, not ever, lose to the disgusting human race!
I refuse to be inferior in any way!
I will not let it go.
I can't let it go... Not ever...
Hmm...
Not ever, huh? Doesn't sound like that's it.
I think she actually wants to understand humans.
That's why she's so desperate to understand
the things about us that make no sense to her.
Hey, Tohru.
First, you gotta find the spoon's center of gravity.
Then, you just use the principle of leverage like this.
There.
Uh?
That's it...?
Once you understand, it seems obvious, huh?
This is fairly simple.
But there are some things that
aren't this easy for everyone.
If you ask me, I think you should focus
on those special things only you can do.
Heh. Yeah, that makes sense. Thanks, Miss Kobayashi.
Heh...
I get it now.
Tohru...
Well then! I'm gonna show you a power only I can use!
Make sure you pay close attention to me!
All right. But no breaking anything, okay?
Nevermind. I won't be able to do anything, then.
The avatar of destruction.
I can make electricity.
Oh.
Now the beautiful assistant has entered the box.
Watch closely!
This is the super magic of instant teleportation!
Here it comes!
This is the moment of the century, folks.
PFFT!!
A maid?!
What the hell just happened? A
maid has appeared from the box!
This isn't what was planned, right?
Hey, will you give me extra, please?
Sweet and sour pork with pineapples?
I hate when they serve this crap.
No! It's too cute!
We're likely to have leftovers...
...so have some extra.
Extra? Extra?! She gave me extra?!
Miss Kobayashi, I learned some new magic!
Wow.
Please take a look at this coin on a string.
Okay.
You will fall deeper and deeper in love with Tohru!
Deep in love with Tohru!
That's not magic and it's not working.