She's been watching school kids a lot lately.
You think she might be wanting to go?
Who, Kanna?
Yes, I would assume so. It's only natural, after all.
Eventually, every dragon wrestles with ideas like death.
Oh, youth!
Uh. What are you talking about?
Kanna's journey to eliminate humanity?
No, jeez. I meant "think she
might be wanting to go to school"?
Oh, right.
I see stuff about school on the Internet all the time.
The Internet? Sure got a hold of you fast.
Hmm.
Hey, Kanna?
Hmm?
Hey, Kobayashi. Did you need something?
No, I was just wondering... Do you want to go to school?
Kobayashi! Hurry up! Come on!
Kanna, stop!
You should treat Miss Kobayashi with more respect!
I don't understand why you need
all this just to go to school.
There's nothing to understand once you recognize the
obvious conspiracy between the
schools and the manufacturer.
Total conspiracy.
That's doubtful on many levels, Tohru.
Not according to the Internet!
So dragons fall for online BS, too.
How about we pick up the basics first?
Okay!
Hello, welcome!
Yep. This is it.
How funny, these school supplies haven't
changed, like, even a little since I was a kid.
No.
What, why no?
They're not very cute.
They're wha...?
Wow, Miss Kobayashi. You're so clueless.
Hmm?
Don't worry 'bout it, though. I've got this!
Why are we here?
Because feathers that have been plucked from living
birds during this time of year produce the best pens!
That's creepy.
No...
Looks like you're clueless, too.
This doesn't make sense.
Back in our world, practically everybody uses quill pens.
I want a cute one, though. A cute one!
Uhh. I think she wants a cute one.
Hmm... I heard about a new store that just opened
outside the shopping district. It should have cute stuff!
Hello, glitter. I'm blinded with sparkling.
Kobayashi, look!
What's this? How am I supposta use it?
You write with it like this.
You'll be using a pencil, though, Kanna.
Miss Kobayashi! How'd I do?!
Uh.
Kobayashi, look.
What's this thing? It looks like a dragons mouth to me.
It's a stapler.
Or it's a torture device...
How'd you jump to that?
And what about this?
C'mon, it's obvious. That is a tool for slave branding.
You use it to mark your property.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi!
Will you please brand me as yours?
No way.
Ah. Look, Lady Tohru. A unicorn.
Mine!
If that unicorn knew about this,
I think it would be very happy.
Part of me wants to ask,
but the other part knows better.
Thanks so much!
Not much left to get, now.
Onward, ho!
Ho!
Do we really have to go here, of all places?
Sorry, there's nowhere else
close to us that sells backpacks.
I can appreciate our situation, but I don't like it.
I can't help but remember back when...
Whatever. We can go by ourselves.
I didn't say I wouldn't go!
Well, Kanna? You decide yet?
Uh-huh.
Surprisingly normal, considering.
Great choice, Kanna.
I had a feeling you'd go with a cursed
backpack soaked in the blood of humans.
Mm-hmm.
That was her reason?!
That'll be 38,000 yen.
It's not made out of gold, is it?
Is that too much?
No, it's fine...
I'm gonna use my card to pay for this.
Of course. We take all forms of payment.
Hi, how're you?
Miss Kobayashi, Kanna's gonna pout
again if we go in another store like this.
We don't have a choice.
This is where the school said we have to go.
Conspiracy.
Let it go.
I think these are the ones on our list.
They all seem the same to me.
That's the point.
They want the kids to all wear the
same thing so they'll all look the same.
Why would they want that?
Hmm. So no one feels different.
Boys, girls, new students.
Everyone is supposed to be exactly the
same as everyone else. It's a big deal.
And what happens when you're different from everyone else?
They eliminate you. It sucks.
I know it might be different for dragons,
but humans aren't that accepting of
people who are different from them.
That's ludicrous.
Yeah. I completely agree with you.
The truth is, people are just terrified.
They fear anything different.
I kind of understand.
Hmm. I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to bring the room down.
You're sweet to worry about me.
Well, Kanna. Looking forward to school?
Mm-hmm.
All right, once we get home,
we prepare for tomorrow!
Yay!
Miss Kobayashi, that's not fair!
You should be holding my hand, too!
Fine, whatever.
Kobayashi!
Look at me!
Whoa! You look amazing!
Super-cute deluxe.
Lady Tohru.
Look! What do you think?
Kanna. Hey, can I borrow that for just a second?
Hmm?
Miss Kobayashi!
Check it out!
What do you think of me?
I think jealousy is not your best look.
I can't believe she wore that
backpack for the rest of the day.
She must be really excited.
I get that she's excited, but this seems a bit excessive.
She may be a dragon, but she's also still a child.
Any idea what Kanna's doing?
She's practicing her writing.
Oh!
So... how's it going?
Huh...?
Maybe it's time to stop practicing.
Good morning!
Yes, yes, good morning, children.
Today, I have a brand-new student
and friend to introduce to you.
This is Kanna Kobayashi.
I'm Kanna, and it's a pleasure to meet you.
She's adorable!
Where are you from, Kanna?
Ushishir Island.
Overseas?
No surprise that Kanna's classroom
introduction is going over so well.
Make sure you watch over Kanna today, okay?
Don't worry. Tohru is on the job!
Good. Let's try this one, now.
Kanna? Do you think you can solve it?
That problem is so lame.
I don't get what she finds so fascinating about school.
Correct. Very good, Kanna.
Such an inefficient way to learn.
Putting those kids in different classes based on
their abilities would help all of them develop faster.
Their game seems to be simply
hitting each other with a ball.
Fitting pastime for barbarians.
Kya!
Yes! Very good, Kanna!
She's showing them no mercy.
Kanna, you're incredible!
You can do anything, huh?
Kanna, do you think we could be friends?
Mm.
Oh, can I be your friend, too?
Hmm.
The truth is people are just terrified.
They fear anything different.
Maybe so, but they clearly try
to ally themselves with the strong.
They may be young, but they're still only human.
Goodbye, have a good evening!
Thank you, kids. You, too!
Yo, Kanna. Kanna Kobayashi.
Hmm?
You are getting way too much attention!
Ugh. Saikawa's acting like a queen again.
Great, thank you for making things so clear!
Now, shut up, no one asked your opinion!
You were saying?
You bet I was! You really piss me off!
You're so cute I just want to hug you forever!
I challenge you, Kanna Kobayashi!
I'll prove to the class that
I'm better than you'll ever be!
Don't fall for it, Kanna!
Saikawa plays dirty and she's a big ol' cheater!
Not to mention she's a sad meanie
who'll never admit she lost anyway.
You shut your stupid, lying mouth!
You wanna try arm-wrestling me?!
I look weak, but I've won karate
tournaments, so I... Oh, uh...
I just... I just wanted to be friends...
Oh, gahwd! I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to make you sad!
The truth is, I just wanna be friends with you, too!
I swear it! Oh, shoot, Saikawa, look what you did!
She is so messed up...
Please don't cry! I have candy! Want some candy?
Uh-oh! We're not allowed to
bring candy to school, Saikawa!
I said, shut up!
Fake crying, huh?
Seems kind of a devious way
to settle things, doncha think?
I would've obliterated them and been done with it.
Hmm.
Why did you decide you wanted to go to school?
I thought it would be fun to watch the kids.
Was it fun, though?
Mm-hmm.
Keep in mind some aspects might not be too fun.
Hmm.
There's no reason for us to try
and be exactly like the humans.
Living among them doesn't mean we have to live as them.
You know what I mean?
I do.
But they're so close by, and we
share our lives with the humans.
Embracing them just feels a lot better than hating them.
Embracing them...
I've seen comrades destroy themselves,
all because acceptance was too foreign,
so they thought hate was their only option.
But there's a choice.
And I think, for now, I'm gonna go with embracing, too.
Ah! So how was your first day?
It was really fun.
That's good to hear.
Miss Kobayashi, I fulfilled my given mission, too!
Please praise me!
You are now praised. Oh, I almost forgot.
For you, Kanna.
Hmm?
But how...?
It's a congratulations.
You should be able to hang it on your backpack.
Miss Kobayashi!
Hmm?
What'd you get me?!
What about me, Miss Kobayashi?! Me?
Ta-dah.
Oh, yay!
So pretty...
What are you doing to your stuff?
I'm labeling it.
They said I was supposed to put nametags on all my things.
Call now for today's special product!
That wasn't too hard.
Huh...?
Why?
How?
Why and how did things get like this?
The story starts one day ago.
This is real good!
You're the best.
No, you are.
Sorry I keep dropping by all the time.
You're checking up on Tohru, aren't you?
Yeah. How'd you know?
Well. You're not alone.
Uh. I'm bored with this game.
I would like to play something else, if you don't mind.
Come on, be honest. You're here to check up on Tohru, too.
I'm home.
Ooh, you survived another day!
Oh, no...
What happened?
A duel.
A duel?
I shall assist you.
I shall kill.
Calm down, ya delinquents!
It happened earlier on the way home.
Kanna.
I decided that, today, I'll go home with you,
so consider yourself honored with my presence.
Hmm. You are very kind, Saikawa.
I like you.
Hmm?
Today, I'm gonna show you the best place to play!
Mm-hmm.
Well? This place is huge, but it's kind
of a hidden spot, so no one ever comes here.
That's the thing you fly with!
What? Fly?
Yeah. In the clouds.
Hmm? Sure, sounds fun.
Let's play on the seesaw.
Sorry about that, girls.
Be more careful, you idiots!
What's wong? Widdle baby fwightened by a widdle ball?
Don't be a jerk. We're sorry.
Sometimes, dodgeball gets crazy.
And? Little kids come here to play, too, so you
should leave if you can't handle your dumb game.
Nowhere else to go.
[We wouldn't leave if there was somewhere else.
It's time for the babies to go home.
For real, dude, who hurt you?
You'll pay.
What?
I challenge you to a dodgeball game tomorrow!
If you lose, you can't play here!
Uh...
You hear that?!
The infant thinks she's gonna defeat us!
Yeah, we're not gonna play with you,
but thanks for the offer we appreciate it.
Why, what's wrong? You scared?
Maybe you're afraid you're gonna get embarrassed
in front of all your nerdy, loser friends?
Try not being so chicken!
What did you say?
Don't listen to her, man.
Or don't listen to that mama's boy!
Huh?
Wanna call your mom to see if she
thinks you can win against us, mama's boy?
Is that what you need? "Help me, Mama, help me!"
You are such a brat.
What's wong?
Are the big, bad boys fwightened by a widdle, baby girl?
Hmph. Pathetic, much?
Fine, snot nose, bring it on!
Don't throw a fit when you lose!
What do I do...?
So you picked a fight and they took you up on it?
How many kids have agreed to help you out?
About zero. Saikawa's not very popular.
I know! I'm the worst!
What to do about it...?
I bet you could still negotiate with them.
No way! I assure you, they must fight!
Under no circumstances shall the
noble and proud dragon be taken lightly!
Do you know how to play?
Yes!
I know, as well. I've played a lot of Explosive Dodgeball.
This isn't that kind of game.
Come on, we can do this!
Yeah!
Don't stress. I'm sure it'll work out.
Hmm...
What's this, squirt?! Had to call in friends?!
We're not gonna go easy on ya, now!
Tohru.
Hmm?
No killing.
'Kay!
I knew how it would end at the start.
From the onset, their abilities... Well, their species.
They were on different levels.
This game was above and beyond one-sided.
It wasn't a win.
It was a massacre.
Damn it!
That's not fair!
You set us up! You're gonna regret this!
Oof, "beat up" is not his color.
Kanna, your friends are incredible!
Hmm. You're right, they're the worst scum ever.
Not untrue, but you could be more delicate.
I could play this game all day long.
Well, what a coincidence. Same here.
Yeah, me three.
I just remembered...
Now, I might be wrong, but have I
yet to win against the two of you?
Think today's the day?
Probably... no.
Huh, this could be real bad.
I wanna play!
Huh?
From that moment forward...
...the playground became a battlefield.
Rah!
So many dragons.
Excellent.
Where did my peaceful, boring,
little life run off to? Meh, whatever.
And that brings us to now.
Don't stress. I'll restore the playground to normal.
And I'll tweak the memories of anyone who saw us.
You're more and more useful to have around.
After that, they took to playing dodgeball on the regular.
Pay more attention to your lower back!
Oh. Is this better?
Think "old lady about to be deserted"!
Nailed it again.
Look, Kanna!
Isn't it super cute?
Oh... Yeah, that's wicked.
Kanna, over here. These are so cool!
Kanna, hey!
Hello, Saikawa, you're wicked.
Okay! Time to start class, kids.
Oh, yeah, that's wicked.
Oh, yeah, that's wicked. Oh, yeah, that's wicked.
What's wicked? What are they talking about?
Kanna, aren't you glad we won the dodgeball game?
Yes.
We almost lost our right to play at the playground!
That's okay.
I'll be happy anywhere if I'm with you, Saikawa.