Wow!
The beaches in this world are pretty. Real pretty!
With so many people, don't you wanna just
mow 'em all down at once, Miss Kobayashi?
Can't say I do.
The ocean here's salty?
Yep, sure is.
That's the same, then.
My favorite thing about swimsuits is that
you can show off as much flesh as you want!
Not accurate or appropriate.
For real?
Shouta, baby, what do you think?
So aggressive!
Way less scary.
Not a compliment, but thanks for the effort, kid.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Hmm?
Yeah?
I need you to come with me...
your swimsuit is way too skimpy.
Hey! Hold on!
Well, that was entirely expected.
They finally let me back out!
Why did you think to bring an extra suit?
I didn't. These're scales.
You guys wearing scale suits, too?
They're cute. I'll give you that.
Thanks! We looked up designs on the Internet.
Aren't you jealous?
Of the suit? No.
Of what's filling it out? Yes.
I wanna go play, please.
Looks like we're gonna go play for a little bit.
What'll you do here without us, though?
Hmm... Probably nothing.
What's the matter, Miss Kobayashi?
You haven't seemed excited all day.
There's a good reason for that.
To be honest, I'm not a huge fan of the beach.
Huh?!
I think you might've been too honest.
Whatever. It's hot, I burn, and sand gets everywhere.
I couldn't agree more. I prefer to be indoors, myself.
If that's true, then why agree
to come out to a beach with us?
I have my reasons!
Primarily, I don't have a whole lot going on this summer.
On top of that, my manager asked
me if I would look after Shouta.
I figured going along with you
guys was the path of least resistance.
Wait, I get it. This is a tsundere thing, am I right?
Not even a little.
I wanna go play now, please.
Oh, right, gotcha. Just a sec.
Uhh...
Sunscreen! First things first!
"I'm an inferior human 'cause my skin
gets damaged by the sun without this stuff!"
Okay, let me start with you, Miss Kobayashi!
Get weird and get fired.
Here you go, Shouta, baby. You don't mind, do you?
Perfect. Have at it!
C'mon.
No, I can't!
Boo. Then let's switch!
All right. Is that good?
What? Is what good?!
Am I coating you good?
I knew it. You are a demon!
Why...?
Bad demon, bad! Stop trying to seduce me!
Lucoa, um...
At this point, you might as well
start acting like you're a demon.
I want to play now, please.
How about watermelon splitting?
I'm in.
Go a little farther right!
No, too far, too far. Go back left.
Go straight. That's right. Okay, stop.
Yay.
Good job, Kanna!
You obliterated every last trace of it.
Well. Whaddaya gonna do?
I wanna swim, now!
Heck yeah. I wanna swim, too!
Hey, be sure that you don't go too far out.
What? How come?
It's dangerous.
Yeah. I guess you're right about that, so okay.
Not too far.
I still remember that time Leviathan
almost killed me, and I don't want that.
What did you do?
I was too far away to see him clearly,
so I accidentally called him Rahab.
Why, you...!
My point was less dragon rage and more, "don't drown."
Oh, yeah, I totally forgot humans don't
have the ability to breathe under water.
Stupid and inferior.
You can breathe under water?
Well, of course!
There's nothing like swimming
to your heart's content, you know?
What, does she have gills now?
Lady Tohru, let's race to the area there.
Sure, I think that's reasonable.
Do you mind giving us the signal, Miss Kobayashi?
Okay. On your marks, get set.
Go!
I forgot to remind them to hold back.
Not too bad, Kanna.
Impressive, Lady Tohru.
I win!
That was too far!
We know. We're sorry.
Well, it's whatever. Are you ready for lunch?
Yeah!
Thank you. It was delicious!
What's next, Lady Tohru?
I dunno.
Miss Kobayashi, what do you...
What's wrong, Miss Kobayashi?
Oh. Nothing.
Just realized that old man hasn't
changed much since the last time I saw him.
When was that?
Back when I was a little kid.
I used to come to this beach with my family a lot.
Family...
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
You okay?
Hmm?
I'm fine.
Miss Kobayashi?
Hmm?
Could you please tell me more about your family?
I mean, that is if you don't mind telling me.
Huh?
I'd appreciate it.
Yeah, okay, sure.
I think we were a normal family.
Y'know, for the most part.
I felt like I was raised normally, at least.
They got me through college, so I can't complain.
After that, though, I left home to go to work.
I call my parents every now and then to catch up.
Tell 'em how I'm doing, stuff like that.
I, uh, I haven't seen them in a while now, though.
And is that considered normal
for a human family in this world?
I guess.
Normal, huh?
Then, why would she welcome a dragon into her home?
And if she's from a normal family, why aren't
most humans as accepting as Miss Kobayashi?
I don't get it.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe humans of this world actually could accept dragons.
Kill them! Humans are evil!
Kill them all!
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. Don't worry.
I'm fine! I just, I feel listless today.
I'm not used to having low energy.
Tohru.
Uh?
Can I ride you?
This is incredible!
I'm glad you're having fun! I am, too!
All right.
Tohru.
Do you think you're starting to get homesick?
No, not particularly.
Well, that makes one of us, then.
Thanks to our discussion, I feel
like I need to go visit my parents.
I'd like to see my parents every now and then.
But it's no big deal.
No? Then what's really bugging you?
I thought for a second about
introducing you to my parents.
You can do that if you want.
No, I can't.
Why not?
Because I'm pretty sure they'd kill you.
Does seem excessive, but, that's most
likely just common sense in your world, huh?
For sure.
From my parents' point of view, I'm
about as far from normal as you can get.
They don't think I have any common sense to speak of.
It's makes me sad.
Hmm...
Talking to Tohru about this kind of stuff
is intense. And yeah. That makes me sad, too.
Certainly drives home the difference between
understanding words and understanding each other.
I've never really considered how
completely different our worlds are.
Although, I bet that's why I always feel like I need
to cherish the time we get to spend together so much.
You know what?
That sounds an awful lot like independence to me.
Independence?
Yep. You've developed your
own unique set of values, Tohru.
So then, you mean I've become an adult?
Who knows? I'm not even sure about me.
Most people don't try to become adults, they just reach a
point where they realize they
can't stay children any longer.
Ooh, that's deep, Miss Kobayashi!
Got one!
Tiny...
Ready to head back?
Sure!
Dragon fireworks?
That's right.
Won 'em in a lottery at the shopping district.
That's it?
Yep.
A real dragon is way cooler than that crap!
Very impressive, Lady Tohru.
See! See!
How's that, Miss Kobayashi, how's that?!
What?
I can't understand anything you're saying right now.
What on Earth is that?
The admission line for Comiket.
And the reason we're around all these
people is to provide cover for Mister Takiya?
Not cover. We just came to help.
Apparently, his other two assistants collapsed.
Ooh, I'm all over this!
With my power, I'll be able
to exterminate them in no time!
Do not.
By the way, was leaving Kanna behind a good idea?
There's a lot of stuff here children shouldn't see.
Thanks, guys! You're saving me! I'm screwed without help.
It's cool. I kinda owe you a few anyway.
I would have thought you'd ask
Fafnir to help you out with this.
Uh, he's participating as a circle.
Huh?!
What? He's a circle?
Sorta?
A circle's a group of people like us.
We sell the art we make to other fans.
It's way fun.
That makes sense.
But why would Fafnir ever do anything like that?
I recommended all kinds of anime and games to him.
At some point he started drawing his own.
He really seems to be getting into this world.
Kobayashi, you can handle sales.
Tohru, I'd really appreciate it
if you could deal with the line.
Sure thing.
Hmph. All right. Fine.
Attention, Ladies and Gentlemen, as of this moment,
the third day of Comic Market has officially begun!
Guys? What's going on?
No running in the hall, please.
Please do not run.
This is bizarre.
It's like they can all barely contain themselves!
Something powerful is holding back their selfish desires.
What in the world?
The new one, please.
Cash or charge?
Cash! Thank you very much.
The new and the previous one, please.
The end of the line for Water
Dragon Shrine starts right here!
Up there, could you guys group closer together, please?
Hard to believe tens of thousands
of individuals are able to take
such unified actions without
any prior exercises or training.
An extremely powerful energy must be at work.
Uh, excuse me.
Who, me?
Yeah, are you, by chance, a cosplayer?
No, by choice, I'm not.
Right, gotcha. I'm sorry. Well, you look awesome.
I figured you were from abroad or something.
I happen to be a real maid wearing a uniform.
Uh. Oh, I get it now. You're just in character.
How fun!
You're wrong. I'm the real deal.
Hey, I understand. It's policy.
If you don't mind, I promise to come
by and take your picture later, okay?
No, wait! I told you that I'm real!
The end of the line for Water Dragon Shrine starts here!
These people are passionate.
Meanwhile, I'm over here feeling like
I'm in a firedrake's stomach.
Thank you, sir. Have a good one!
I can't believe it's this insane.
Comiket is not to be underestimated.
Still, though...
What in the world could be attracting this
many people and keeping them all in check?
It's beyond me... and kinda terrifying.
Tohru!
Oh?
Thank you so much for your help!
Need a drink?
I've been waiting for this!
Bug collecting.
Cicada...
...is...
...very...
...crunchy.
Let's see...
We should be getting close.
What are you looking for?
Trying to find Fafnir.
I figured I should stop by and
say hi while I'm on my break.
If you say anything, I'll kill you.
Don't be fussy. Besides, you're the one who looks dead.
It's no fun, but this is what it's like for first-timers.
Mind if I, um, look at your book?
Heh. Help yourself.
"Curse Anthology."
You... Fafnir!
You've printed real, effective curses!
You even tell how to inflict them!
You could curse someone to death if you read this aloud!
You what?
That's all you're charging?!
Wow, talk about a bargain.
So, uh, maybe... you shouldn't be selling that to people.
There are so many cosplayers here.
I think that's my favorite part. It's fun to watch.
You'd be surprised how many races from
my world are represented by these humans.
For them, it's more about pretending
to be characters from anime and manga.
If you wanted to, you could totally do that.
I am a proper maid, thank you!
No matter how you dress me up, I
will always be your loyal sex slave.
Uh... That's not proper or maid.
What's up?
There's a goblin, a witch, and a sahuagin over there.
Wonder what they're from.
Nothing. They're real.
Huh?
They're not dressed up in costumes, and they're not human.
Huh?!
Excuse me? Yes, hello. I just had a
real quick question for the three of you.
Oh, hi. Can I assume you're like us?
Yes. I was wondering what you're doing here?
I like to come to these to spread my wings.
Same here.
I normally live my life disguised as a human.
But being able to come to events like
this gives me a chance to enjoy my real form.
I see that.
Why not take a chance and join us, dear?
You can let your real form be seen while also being safe!
No. That'd be impossible.
I mean, I'm a dragon.
Dragon?!
Yes?
You're a real damn monster?
I guess?
And you... You could eat us all if you wanted?
Huh?
Run!
No running!
Dragons must do some crazy stuff.
Don't believe them...
Huh?
When dragons get hungry, we only
eat as much as necessary to survive.
And this world is survival of the fittest anyway!
So you're not denying anything, just explaining it?
Hey, you! Could you come with me, please?
You're costume's too skimpy.
Did you not read the participant's guide?
I didn't expect Lucoa to show up.
Hey...
Skimpy is as skimpy does.
Now that I look closer, there's more than I first thought.
Beings in their true form, I mean.
Are there a lot?
Yes.
Those that've had a greater presence
while they were here have left records
of their stays in this world on
several different levels for tourists.
Like Fafnir and Lucoa. I'm sure you've heard of some.
I, umm... I think...
Hmm?
I think, that... I wanna be in my real form.
At least partly, just for a bit.
Please...?
As long as you can do it and stay out of trouble.
It's fine with me.
Sorry that took so long!
Can I take your picture like that?
Yes!
Excuse me! Can I take one, too?
Hey, me, too!
Uh?
Over here! Can you look this way please?
Look over here, next, please!
Crap, our break's almost over.
Stay there and just move your head this way!
Oh, well.
See? Told ya! I came for your pic like I promised!
Right. Hello. How's it going?
Uh, to be honest,
it's been going pretty rough for me.
But I'm hanging in there!
Hey, so.
From my perspective, it seems like everyone in this place
has been drawn here by something with a lot of power.
Do you have any idea what that something might be?
Uh...
I'm not sure, but uh... Well, it's for sure special.
And it's only right here in this moment.
Might as well make the most of it.
Whatever this is, it's making a lot of people happy.
Hmm?
Yes, you're right.
Might as well make the most of it.
Hey, buddy.
Will you take the picture already?
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Uh-oh! Geh!
Don't tell me there's another line forming?
As of right now,
Comic Market 90 is officially over.
Thank you everyone for your participation.
We hope to see you all again in the winter
for the next epic Comiket! Thank you again!
I'm back.
You survived!
And don't worry, we managed fine without you after lunch.
I'm so sorry.
I honestly never intended to ditch you.
I know, it's fine.
Oh, hey, Fafnir, how'd your book sell?
Apparently, not all that well.
All right, so what did you
think of your first ever Comiket?
Hmm? Well, let's see...
Mainly, it just reconfirmed my love for you,
Miss Kobayashi.
Huh?
Thank you, ladies! You were a huge help
today. Like, the best assistants ever!
And if it's no trouble, I'd
love your help again this winter!
Hell no, I'm done with this!
Huh...?
What do you think we should print for our next thin book?
How about a dragon maid girl?
That sounds great!
So they gave you "free studies"?
Mm-hmm. It's my summer homework.
What do you think I should do?
Well, if I were you.
I would probably choose something mysterious.
Something that I'd like to know more
about so I didn't get bored with it.
Okay. That makes sense.
Whatcha doing, Kanna?
Studying you. Act natural.
Huh?
You know, Kobayashi, there's a lot
of talk about Tohru on the Internet.
Yeah, I bet.
They mentioned you, too. They said
there was a sales lady with dead-fish eyes.
Sorry 'bout that.
And they got turned on by those eyes.
And now I'm creeped out.