Good morning!
Your coffee's ready, Miss Kobayashi.
Just what I needed. Thanks.
Kanna, you'll have to eat faster
than that if you wanna be on time.
'key.
I made you some hot milk.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi?
I'm sure you have something
particular you want for dinner, yeah?
Hmm... Not really.
Anything works for me!
Except for that.
Still no tail?
Tohru, what about you? What would you like to eat?
What would I like?
Uh... Omurice , I guess.
Yummy!
For real?
Yes, let's do that!
Ok!
It's gonna be delicious, right?
You betcha! Tohru's on it!
So, what time do you expect
to be getting home this evening?
Hopefully not too late.
I hope that, too.
See you later, Lady Tohru.
I'm heading out, too.
See ya! Have a good day!
All right! Here I go!
Time to get my maid on!
Cleaning, cleaning, la la la.
Beat the dust and de-de-destroy it!
No trash or fleck of dust will be left behind!
Now clean, now clean clean everything.
Ugh! What?
Oh, no, you did not.
Death, death, death to the world!
Oh! Um...
Bathroom, check!
Bedrooms, check!
Entrance, check!
Rooster, check!
Living room, check!
Classic Tohru! Perfect timing on the laundry, too!
I bet these will dry fairly
quickly with all this sunshine today.
Coming!
Just need your stamp, please.
Thank you for all your hard work.
You're welcome. Thank you!
Must be that cushion to help with
Miss Kobayashi's lower back pain.
Good.
I finished everything I needed to.
All that's left now is to make the omurice for dinner.
This is all for Miss Kobayashi.
It's gonna be delicious, right?
Tonight's dinner will be the best omurice ever!
I need to do a trial run.
Not too bad!
Good work, me.
Fluffy, juicy eggs,
hot rice with ketchup,
and all at restaurant quality.
As for the taste?
Average?!
It's not that it tastes bad, it's just that...
It's gonna be delicious, right?
It's just that I want it to be more special than average.
And she made it clear she didn't want any of my tail.
Coming!
Hey.
Oh, hi! What are you doing here, Lucoa?
To see you and bring these.
Want some snacks?
Duh. Thank you!
What are you wearing that for?
Oh, those pesky patriarchal societal
demands were getting on my nerves,
so I changed clothes.
Give it a week, they'll be begging you to change back.
Huh?
You can come on in if you want.
Okay, I think I will. Thank you!
No wonder that little shop had such awesome reviews.
Would you like me to make you some more tea?
Oh. No, I gotta go, thanks, though.
Sure! I was just...
I was in the middle of making trial batches
of omurice for Miss Kobayashi for dinner, and...
Well, do you know any cooking techniques
that might make it taste a bit better?
Huh. Making omurice better?
The simplest thing I can think of to do
is to use the best ingredients you can find.
Yes, that's brilliant!
See ya later!
Thanks for the tea, it was heavenly.
I'm sure you meant that as a compliment.
The best ingredients.
It's so expensive.
Let's see. That plus...
...the best rice, vegetables, and eggs.
Uh! Wait. I'm over budget?!
Are you shopping for dinner tonight, Tohru?
Oh. Mister Tatsuta.
Yes, but this chicken is expensive, don't you think?
Well, that's because it's locally
raised, free-range, and organic.
I don't suppose you could give me a discount?
Sorry, it's already priced as low as I can go.
Not even a little discount?
I can't. If I go any lower
than this, I'll be losing money.
I understand.
But I do want to thank you
for doing the Christmas show.
So I could give you some off on these cuts.
Average?!
Average cuts would defeat the point.
The point of what?
It's gonna be delicious, right?
I have no other options.
Hereabouts should be good.
I'm back from school!
Welcome home, Kanna!
Lady Tohru. What'd you do?
I picked up ingredients for omurice .
And you had to go back to do that?
Just for a second.
Goodness. So, whose eggs are these?
Oh, those? I got them from Gullinkambi's nest.
Really? The rooster who is Valhalla's alarm clock?
Yep.
Doo-a-doodle-cock!
They're unbelievably good!
They are?
An Einhairjar told me they were the
best quality eggs in anywhere ever.
And this?
That's uh.
That's fresh spring water from an elven village.
I plan to use it to boil the rice.
It's pure!
Only problem is I've fought with the elves before.
So I kinda snuck in and took it.
Wow. They have every right to kill you over that.
I also grabbed some meat from bull demons.
As well as fruits that are in season over there.
Where did you get the rice and vegetables?
I thought it would be best to just
use the ones they already have here.
Good call. The rice in this world is out of this world.
Yeah, because they're using magic.
Apparently, it's what's known as "selective breeding."
I should see if I could get someone
to teach me that incantation sometime.
Now, then.
Time to get this cooking party started!
Will you help me get this perfect, Kanna?
Yeah!
Growl!
Out with bad demon,
and in with good blessings!
Roar!
Out with bad demon,
and in with good blessings!
Lucoa!
What's wrong?
Was Shouta-baby worried about me?
No, he wasn't! Shut up!
Aw...
Ugh, I'm so exhausted.
Oh. That's right.
Tonight's dinner is omurice .
That was the first normal meal Tohru
cooked me, now that I think about it.
Dinner's ready, Miss Kobayashi.
She presented it to me with such confidence.
And it was pretty good, too.
Before that, everything she made was so weird.
Either way, it's been nice.
I honestly can't remember the last time
someone was willing to cook for me at all,
much less with that level of excitement.
I remember telling her the omurice was just okay.
Today, I won't.
I'll tell her... that it's good.
Hey, hurry up and get it to me!
Forget about that, you need to fix this error!
Kobayashi! It's almost deadline time!
I know!
Kobayashi! Error alert!
Fixing them now, sir.
Kobayashi! Help over here.
On my way, sir!
Kobayashi! Kobayashi! Kobayashi!
Shut up!
Gimme another one!
Coming up.
There goes my stop!
I don't know where I'm going to!
The mountain sounds good. Air's clear here.
What? Bears! Bring it on!
Tasty beary bears!
Oh man! It's pitch dark black! Can't see!
You shall not pass!
Human. Out of what hole dids't thou crawl?
Whoa! A dragon, ooh, hug me!
Depart, insolent human!
Otherwise, I shall eat you!
Alas. I am going to die, as well.
How tragic it is the last
being I meet is a pathetic human.
Hey, do you ever get bored listening to yourself talk?
Is froufrou lingo like, your thing?
How dare you?
You want me to pull that out?
Huh? Well...
No! You fool!
If a mere human touches God's sword, their mind shall be torn.
I dunno about all that.
But if God exists, then...
...he should exteeeend...
...my stupid deadline......right now!
Aaah!
I know this is just my dream, but...
...why does a dragon gotta be such a big, jerk-baby?!
Apologies. You saved me regardless, and it is appreciated.
I was defeated in battle with the
gods, and barely escaped to this world.
I imagine you only managed to remove
that sword because you lack faith.
I am truly grateful.
Don't judge on prejudices- yours!
Boop, boop, boop.
Wanna drink?
Sure you do! Drink with me, dragon!
Drink with me, and listen to my story!
Why won't you drink?
So you're a lady dragon, then?
Yes. I am female.
To be honest, I detest using this spell, but...
Ooh! You're down to drank!
Yay! Just us girls, let's go!
You're a girl?
Yes, Rude Dragon!
I'm sorry.
...to let me fondle your tits.
It's okay to be curious even though
society pressures me to say I'm not!
I can?
For real! I work hard and for what?
I'm telling ya, this whole world is unfair, man!
Yeah, keep preaching sister!
Let me bring an end to this place for you!
And what the hell?
Your subordinate, your problem!
Do not assume all dragons are really lolicons
who randomly demand villages' virgin daughters!
Nights like this are when I wonder why I'm all alone.
Me, too.
But I truly am alone here. There's no one.
Just me.
Do you have anywhere to go?
No.
But to be fair, I have been alone from the start.
Huh. So, wanna stay with me, dragon?
Yes, I do!
You can be my maid!
Your what?
Listen! We're not talking about just a simple servant here!
Seriously, you can have house maids,
laundry maids, all kinds of maids.
And it takes major training it's
not all those posers at maid cafés!
Oh.
My name's Kobayashi.
My name's Tohru.
Hello, Tohru!
Look, I don't mean to shade maid
cafés, they're fine for what they are,
but they help  contribute to the
maid profession being taken lightly.
Oborozuka. Oborozuka.
Crazy.
I feel like I dreamt about something important.
I'm home.
Kobayashi!
Yay! Welcome back home!
We just finished the omurice !
I helped make it!
Oh!
It's gonna be great!
The omurice was delicious.
But I was so busy pointing out all the obvious issues.
I sorta forgot to tell her how good it was.
Thanks for coming out of nowhere, rain!
I'm back!
Remember this morning when they said, "No chance of rain."
Takiya, help me.
It's guerrilla warfare.
Time to ambush.
Yeah, sure.
I guess we'll be having this for lunch for a while.
He's so cute! Is it okay if I pet him?
Of course!
Good grief, that's ridiculous.
Come on. You're squishing us!
What simple pets, giving such affection to their humans.
Yeah, you're one to talk.
Kanna.
No.
Speaking of the nearness of me,
were there any humans in your old
world you were particularly close to?
Humans in my world? I guess so, kinda.
There is one human I can think of.
You could say I associated with
them, if only for a little while.
Really? What were they like?
Heh. If you'll excuse me.
I'm going to have to talk a lot about myself now.
I first met that human in a
deserted village that was in ruins.
This should work as my home for a while.
It's rare to encounter a dragon in a place like this!
I'm actually only here to hide out, myself.
Do you mind if I stay a short time?
You're a bandit?
Yes, that's right. I mistook a noble
for a merchant and attacked their party.
Now, I'm on the run!
My comrades have been captured, leaving me alone.
So I'm currently debating my
options on where I should go next.
Do you believe I care?
I could save you time and kill you.
How dare you laugh at me!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I mean no offense, Dragon, but you're not
very used to threatening people, are you?
Excuse me?
It's just not very convincing, sorry!
'Tis not just a threat, human!
See what I mean?
So. It's okay, then?
You'll let me stay for a while?
Do as you please.
Thank you!
Thinking back on it now, I could've
just left and found somewhere else.
But in that moment... I guess...
I couldn't allow myself to yield to a human.
Hey, so... you're a dragon, right?
What's that kind of life like?
What do you mean?
You know, like how you can fly.
And you possess so much power
you'll pretty much never lose a fight.
I wish I knew what it was like to live so freely.
Must be wondrous.
Uh! Hey! I'm talking!
At the time, I found myself thinking.
What was my freedom like?
I had never thought of myself as "free" before then.
I was born with the chaos faction.
I lived with chaos, and I fought the divine.
If that all ended, would I be free?
Would it ever end?
Even if it did end, and I was free, what would I do?
What would you do if you had my freedom?
I'd be a maid!
A maid?
Yes! A maid.
I'd wear the cutest maid outfit.
I'd greet every single guest with my very best smile,
and I would totally fall in love with my master.
You would willingly enslave yourself?
Yep! But that's kinda the point!
I'd get to have a choice!
Mine!
Had I chosen it, my life would be so different, y'know?
Even now, if I could make my own
decision between the two options.
At least I could choose to stay
a bandit or choose to be a slave.
I see.
Right?
I realized that I had never made my own choice, either.
But I hadn't been as bothered by it as she was.
Since there wasn't anyone else I wanted to see,
I allowed the girl to stay and chatted with her for a while.
I'm probably good to go.
You are leaving?
I think I'll cross over the mountains and see
if I can get into a nation bordering this one.
I'm sure something'll work out for me.
Oh, do you mind? Can I ride you real quick?
Of course not! I shall never let a human ride me!
Selfish! Selfish!
Say what you will. I would die first!
I hope to see you again.
Goodbye, Dragon! And thank you.
For what?
For spending time with me.
She left after that.
The annoying human was finally gone.
At least, that's how I should have felt.
But instead, I felt a little sad.
I'm sure. Do you think that person
might have something to do with
why you decided to become my maid?
Probably.
I don't say this sort of thing often, but
I don't think I'd mind seeing that human again.
I get that.
Yeah?
Oh, by the way, Tohru.
The way you used to talk sounds like an old man.
Huh? Well, I think it's fancy!
Whatever.
How nice.
The weather's perfect.
Oooh. I think I get that.
I've thoroughly blended in to this world.
Meh. Is what it is.
Tohru, do you think that bandit girl is still alive?
Who knows?
But if she is, I bet she's serving as a maid.
Same as you, then.
Exactly.
Either way, I hope she's well.
I hope so, too.