The sports festival is coming up soon.
Be sure you give that information I just
handed out to your parents, okay, kids?
Hey, Saikawa?
What's this sports festival thing?
Hold up. Are you telling me you
didn't have them where you're from?
Oh, my gosh, a sports festival is,
like, one of the most fun things ever.
There's running.
Running?
Ball-tossing.
Ball-tossing?
Tug-of-War.
Tug-of-War?
Yeah, and lots of other events where
the whole class teams up together!
Our parents get to come and watch for the whole day, too!
Like, you get to eat lunch with them and everything!
And you're, like, the best at sports,
so I bet you'll win it all and be the hero of the day!
I mean, your mom's gonna be
beyond proud of you after this!
Gotta work that day. Can't.
Kobayashi... Take the day off for me...
Please...?
Sorry, I can't do that.
Kanna, Miss Kobayashi's in the middle of her
death march and on the verge of facing Hades.
Give it up already.
No!
Also, what's a sports festival?
It's when you train alongside your
peers to defeat strong opponents.
No, I think that's a bit exaggerated.
Defeat Hades fast, Kobayashi!
Then you can come watch me.
Don't be so selfish.
Besides, I'll come with you to watch the sports.
No...
Why's it gotta be Miss Kobayashi, anyway?
What am I, chopped liver?
No, it's not you, it's just that Saikawa said
our parents could come with us for the day.
You're like my big sister.
Kobayashi's like a mom.
Reminder: I'm not old enough to be Kanna's mom.
Although...
Some of my classmates do have kids already.
Miss Kobayashi, you hang in there!
At any rate, I can't go.
Sorry, but you'll have to make do with Tohru.
Great. "Make do."
Forget it!
Ah, Kanna!
I never thought a parent showing
up or not was that big of a deal.
To start off with, it's not like I'm Kanna's
mother. I'm just a random human she met.
I don't think that matters to her much
because she's been treating you
like a mom-type figure for a while now.
But why?
I can barely be around people.
How could I be a good mother?
This is stupid.
I never had both my parents make it to sports festivals.
They were always too busy working.
I never got upset, either. I knew they had to support us.
Well, Kanna's parents basically gave her free rein.
They felt a dragon would grow up strong all on its own.
Since she bears the name Kanna Kamui,
I'm sure they told her she had
to make sure to be super strong.
But what she wanted was her parents' attention,
which is why she pulled all those silly pranks.
It just got her banished to this world.
Makes sense she'd want you to spoil
her and give her that attention, now.
I get what you're saying, but I still just...
Hey, good morning, Kanna. Something wrong?
Kobayashi won't come to the sports festival.
Really? Wow. It's okay.
There's way more to the day than just parents!
We get to work together with the
whole class to win, and that's super fun.
It does sound fun.
Except your version of "work
together" and ours is totally different.
You shut up! No one asked you!
No one has to ask me for my opinion for me to give it.
Why are you still talking?!
Oh, my god, shut up!
Sports festival?
Bad luck that it falls directly
on our delivery deadline day, huh?
Yeah, but I'm kinda not sure if there's
really any need for me to go in the first place.
Do you not wanna go?
Hmm... No, it's not that.
But I think it would be nice if I could go.
Hmm? What is it?
Oh, you know, just my first time seeing
you worry about something like this.
Seriously?
Hmm. Oh. I guess so.
Well, I think it's more a question of
do you want to go, rather than can you go.
So do I want to go?
La, la, la, I'm the cutest, most
adorable maid forever and ever!
Hey, I'm home.
Oh, I didn't hear you come in.
Kanna, are you still in a bad mood?
You should let it go.
Lady Tohru. Perception block me.
Use perception block on me.
I'm back, guys.
Welcome home.
I'll get your dinner ready.
Kobayashi?
Don't worry about it.
Coming to the sports festival, I mean.
It'll still be fun to be able to
work together with everyone in my class.
It's fine. And I hope you make your deadline okay.
Oh. Thanks.
Good night.
So, um...
Kanna might have used my perception blocking
to go secretly observe you at your work today.
I know I've felt like this before.
Right. It's guilt.
Just like with Tohru.
Tohru.
That's me.
Starting tomorrow, I'll be getting home even later.
Do you mean...?
Okay!
35! 36! 37!
38! 39! 40...
'Kay! Great work, kids, but that's enough for today.
You should all be so proud of yourselves!
Look at how long you can jump, now!
All we have to do is keep this up,
and we'll win the sports festival, easy!
Yeah!
Kanna, we're not gonna let 'em down, are we?
No way.
You're tearing it up.
Trying.
Going to the sports festival, then?
Decide that you want to go?
Nope. Decided that I ought to go.
Lemme help. Tell me whatcha need.
Thanks. You're awesome.
I know.
And, next drinking night is on you.
Yes, it is.
I'll be there tomorrow.
Really?
Yep, really.
You beat Hades already?
Mm-hmm. I sure did.
I love you, Kobayashi!
That's so cute.
I forget she's still just a child.
What do they expect me to do?
What do I do...?
I could go for both!
No, that would go over my daily limit! I can't!
But, still...
Oh, god...
Look, ma'am. We really need you to make a decision.
Yes, I know that! I'm trying to!
Welcome to the 43rd annual
Oborozuka Elementary Sports Festival!
The events will begin now!
First up on the program is the opening parade!
Oh, look! There's Kanna!
Where? I don't see her.
She's looking our way.
Hey!
Yeah, I bet she wants to make sure that I showed up.
Riko!
Little Miss!
You're gonna do great!
Shouta, baby!
Oh, Miss Lucoa's here, too.
I'll be right here cheering for you! Hooray, Shouta!
The pledge: We athletes hereby pledge
to honor the spirit of good sportsmanship
and compete fair and square with all
participants until the very end of the competition!
Fifth on today's program is the
three-legged race by the third graders.
You can do it, Kanna!
No pressure, though!
Riko! You've got this!
Do your best!
Ready...
Um, okay, let's tie our legs together, now.
Done.
Yeah, thank you, Kanna. You're the best.
Still have to hold on to each other's shoulders.
Okay, next pair.
Come on, Saikawa. It's our turn to go.
I-I'm so sorry, Kanna.
I was just way too happy.
That's all right, Saikawa.
We're gonna get 'em next time.
Jeez, Riko, what are you doing out there?
Seventh on our program today is
the fifth graders' treasure hunt.
What? You want me?
Yep. Perfect.
Shouta, your older sister's incredible!
Mm... Yeah...
We'll now be taking a break for lunch.
Students and parents, please enjoy your time together!
Everyone make sure you're careful of heat
stroke and drinking lots and lots of water.
We'll see you back in a bit!
Oh, my gosh! This looks yummy!
Yeah, it does.
I'm not just your everyday dragon maid!
Thank you.
Lady Tohru, it's good.
Thank you for saying so.
Miss Kobayashi?
Say, "ah."
Tohru... What kind of meat is that?
Knew it.
Yeah, this lunch really is especially tasty.
I'm glad you like it.
Eat enough to make sure you have lots of energy!
We'll turn things around after this.
What do they expect me to do?
What do I do?
How am I supposed to choose just one
from over ten different combinations?
I could go for variations of 'em all!
No, then I wouldn't last.
But, still...
Oh, god!
There's the pumpkin and sweet potato.
But chestnut's hard to pass.
The surprising pairing of grape
and pear would be good, wouldn't it?
No, wait. Chestnut.
It's now time to start today's afternoon segment.
Coming up 15th in our program,
we have the third graders' jump rope.
Everyone ready?
And... go!
1!
2!
3!
4!
Go, Kanna!
Jump, Kanna, jump!
Riko, keep those feet up!
Do your best, Little Miss!
22!
23!
Classes 1 and 4 have tripped on their ropes!
42.
43.
Uh-oh, Class 3 has tripped on their rope, now!
But watch Class 2! They're still going strong!
55.
56.
57.
58.
Keep on jumping!
Don't stop, now!
Finished!
Class 3-2 wins!
Did you see that? We just won!
Talk about impressive.
Nineteenth on today's program,
the fifth grade boys' calvalry battle.
Shouta, baby! You can do it!
Kick their tushies!
Begin!
Hooray! Go, Shouta!
Get 'em, baby!
Take 'em down!
Finished!
Class 3 with an overwhelming victory!
Shouta, you're so lucky!
Your sister's awesome!
Mm. Yeah.
Now for our 20th event,
the third graders' tug of war!
Class 1 and 2. Ready?
Go!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Come on, Kanna!
Win the tug of war!
Focus, sweetie!
Do your best!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
The winner is...
...Class Two! Congrats!
Saikawa, can you believe? We won it!
Hooray!
Yeah! She's doing amazing!
Keep up that winning pace, kiddos!
Kanna's class has made it
all the way up to second place.
First after this game.
Ooh! It's about to start!
Thirty-second in today's
program, the third graders' relay!
Hey, Kanna.
If we take first place here, we'll win!
This will be the final event for the third graders.
Family and friends, they're going to
need your support now more than ever!
First female runners.
Take position!
Ready...
Go, Iida! Get it!
You can do it, Iida!
All the classes have started strong.
Right now, Class 1 holds the lead.
Behind them are Class 2, 4, and 3 bringing up the rear.
The baton's passed to the second runner.
Makishima, keep up the pace!
Saikawa, you're gonna do great!
Well, yeah.
I'll be passing you the baton from first place!
What a race!
Class 1 and 2 are currently neck and neck!
Good job, ladies! Keep it up!
Here, I, go!
Wow, Class 2 is closing in fast.
And now they've passed Class 1!
Oh, no! What a disappointment.
Class 2 dropped the baton!
Class 1 is back in the lead.
Behind them are Class 4, then 3, and last place is 2.
I'm sorry!
I got this!
The anchors are all fighting for the win,
but look at Class 2 go!
She's passing the others with no problem.
She's so fast.
Just one more!
You can do it!
Kanna!
Finish!
The winner: Class 2!
You're the best, Kanna!
I'm not kidding. That was incredible!
You were so cool!
Kanna!
You licked me!
But, um... I'm sorry.
I messed up real bad...
No, you kept running. If you'd given up,
there's no way I could've passed all of them.
Thanks for being such a good teammate.
Oh, Kanna!
Here you go. You were so good.
Thanks. I had a lot of fun.
You worked hard out there, too.
I know. Everyone in our class worked
hard, that's why we were able to win.
I imagine it's less than satisfying not
being able to go full out like you normally do.
No, it was fine.
I like being with the other kids.
Kobayashi.
Thank you so much for coming today, really.
You are very welcome.
And thank you for lunch, Lady Tohru.
No problem! Heh! It was hardly anything.
Participating in a sports festival as a guardian?
What in the world have I become?
And when did this change even happen?
Although, I suppose it would be rather
nice to let loose a little bit more today.
I agree.
I'm so down. It's been too long.
Let's get to it, then.
Hey, I wanna play, too!
Oh, how fun!
All three of us together!
That okay, Miss Kobayashi?
Yeah, sure, as long as you go
where you don't bother anyone.
Lady Tohru, where should we go?
Let's use the same place we did last time.
Oh, dragons.
Which should I choose...?
Which should I choose?
Which should I choose?!
Which?!
Why?!
Why must the stupid products of man trouble me so?!
Humans are just...
...terrifying.
I'm the maid Georgie, servant of the Saikawa family.
I'm Shouta's familiar.
You can just call me Lucoa.
Familiar?
Yeah.
It seems we both have somewhat unique hobbies, huh?