I gotta pee.
Huh?
Too close!
Someone's here!
Sorry, Kobayashi.
No, it's fine, don't worry about it.
Hey, it's beer time!
Whoops, excuse me a second!
Is there any juice?
I'm officially over this.
You called looking for a three-bedroom apartment?
Yes. I'd like one as close to this area as possible.
How's this?
Hmm.
They all kinda look the same to me.
This one has a bonus feature:
The rooftop is actually a common area shared by tenants.
Really.
The sky's so vast!
It feels amazing!
What do you think?
Well...
I guess we'll take it.
We've gotta get this place ready for the move.
First, we clean.
Yeah!
Cleaning, cleaning, la la la.
Beat the dust and de-de-destroy it!
What is she singing?
No dust will be left behind!
New clean, clean everything.
If not, then death, death, death to the world!
Are you trying to freak me out?!
Hmm?
So as a dragon, do you like being clean?
I suppose so.
I like to take baths a lot as well as brush my teeth.
You brush your teeth?
Do you have like a dragon-sized toothbrush or something?
No, I use my claws to pick out the bugs.
Bugs? But what about the bacteria?
Yeah. They're so small, I don't really notice them.
Bet it's not easy to have such a huge body.
True. Finding somewhere to live was horrible.
That figures. What did you finally go with?
Sometimes caves.
Sometimes ruins.
Sometimes mountains.
I've even slept in the sky a few times.
Seems dangerous!
Although, that would make living anywhere a breeze.
Whoa.
Actually, no.
Why is that funny?
Anyway, if I stayed in one
place too long, humans showed up.
They're the worst.
You were, like, a rare monster.
The point is, my body kept getting dirty.
But I barely got the opportunity to bathe at all.
Ew.
When worse came to worst, we
would have to lick each other clean.
Huh?!
Kanna and I've done that before.
Ugh! That is inappropriate
behavior for humans!
Maybe so.
But most dragons couldn't care
less about all the silly human rules.
We don't get sick or unhealthy either way.
Wow. Okay, I'm jealous of that.
You know what? You're a very sloppy person.
You leave beer cans scattered all over,
and your clothes stay right where you took them off.
What does it matter what I do?
That's what I liked so much about living alone.
Also, your books are not in any order that I know about.
Now that's just being too picky!
Ahem.
Fine, I can overlook the catastrophe of books.
However, you can at least clean up your trash and clothes.
Don't forget this is my home.
You don't want Kanna to pick
up those nasty habits, do you?
No...
My father must have felt exactly
like this when my mother yelled at him.
Hmph. You know, Tohru.
I keep leaving crap around
because I'm happy you're here, okay?
I like that you clean up.
I mean, that stuff's basically a cakewalk for
a mighty and powerful dragon like you, right?
Uh-huh. It is!
Tohru, I'd love it if you kept helping out...
...if you want.
I do want! I do! Yes!
So pretty.
Scoundrel Kobayashi.
All right, next up is packing.
Right!
I know almost all of these things belong to me.
Sorry for asking you to help out.
Never fear. You can ask anything at all of me!
I'll do my best, too!
Hmm?
Focus, Kanna. Stop fooling around...
Chibi Kobayashi! Aah!
Those dead-fish eyes are killing me... they're so cute!
There's something wrong with you.
Can you focus for five seconds, please?
What? I had no clue I still had this.
Focus.
Me?! I'm all focus!
Miss Kobayashi!
Hmm?
Tell me this maid outfit is yours!
Yeah, that's mine.
Will you please, oh, please try it on for me?! I want
to see if you're as adorable in it as I know you'll be!
No.
Why? You bought it so you could wear it, didn't you?
Yeah, but as soon as I saw my reflection,
I realized I looked idiotic. I'll never wear that again.
Then would you mind if I wore it?
Hmm? Not at all.
Hooray! Thank you!
So, how do I look?
Lovely, lady Tohru!
Mm-hmm! I think it looks great, too.
I can't say I disagree! Thanks!
Although, your clothes seem to always
be a bit too tight in the chest for me.
Speaking of...
Hmm?
There's no way in hell you're really just a D.
I'm a D for a dragon if that helps.
Ah! Beer, win!
Great work today, you guys!
Yes. You two are so awesome!
Finally, time for a bath.
What happened to the towels and clean
clothes I laid out in the bathroom?
I packed all of it up in a box for you!
Huh?
Huh...?
You know which box that is, by chance?
Good morning!
Sansan Moving Service at your service!
Great. Go to town, boys.
So this is a car, huh?
Let's figure out how we're gonna use this space.
Living room, obviously.
Office in here? Sound good?
I think I'll take this one as my bedroom.
Last, but not least...
You two will get to share this room!
Huh?
Wait this is our room?
Yep. You can do whatever you want with it.
Yay!
A whole new life.
Hmm?
Shall I wash your back for you?
What? No, I'm fine.
You said you liked it when I made things clean.
That is what you said, right?
Ugh, that's your angle? Okay, fine, come on in.
Okay.
I have a question.
Yes?
Wouldn't it be easier for you to
wash your body in your human form?
Technically, yes. But I can't be as thorough.
All of the confusing and finicky
rules in this world don't help, either.
I find the whole thing a little stifling.
You don't like your human form, do you?
Yes!
And no, it's complicated.
Sure.
Knock, knock. I'm coming in!
Lady Tohru, wash me, too?
Of course I will!
Ugh, too close!
Here I go!
Morning, Tohru.
Hey, Miss Kobayashi! Hope you slept well!
Tohru.
Uh, yes?
Want me to wash you as a thanks for yesterday?
Do I?
Well, hurry up.
What? Okay!
Thank you... This is incredible...
Feels like I'm washing a car.
Oh, thank you.
Miss Kobayashi, you're the best.
You're welcome, Tohru.
This is the old apartment!
Damn it, why am I so stupid...?
Tohru, that's way too loud!
Huh?
Or not.
Do you believe me to be a loud person?
No, I'm sorry.
Kobayashi, is your hangover making your head hurt?
Yeah...
I can't believe I feel like this on my day off.
The noises sound like they're
coming from both neighbors and above.
Would you like me to speak with them about it?
Actually, if you would, that would be great.
Make sure your horns don't stick out, though.
Sure, no problem!
And if they refuse to listen to me, I'll
just murder, dismember, and pulverize them!
Seems excessive.
I'll start with Miss Sasakibe on our right.
Coming.
Hello. Oh. You're from next door.
I'm Tohru. How are you?
I'm good, thanks. Did you need something?
Well... we've been hearing some really loud noises,
so I decided to come check it out.
I didn't realize I was that loud.
What are you doing? Pillaging?
Just cooking.
Huh...?
Stay here a quick minute.
Here, allow me to share some. Stewed rapeseed blossoms.
Wow, thank you so much!
And if it wouldn't be too much trouble,
would you try keeping the noise down?
Sure.
How could this make such a racket?
Now for Mister Yana on the left side.
What? I'm playing music.
Playing music?
Yeah, want to listen?
Are you the god of the underworld because
you sound like Hades crushing Hercules.
Best compliment ever. Rock on.
Anyways, please try to keep the volume down.
Mm-hmm.
Last is Mister Sone on the floor above.
I'm sorry, but I have to use a drill for work.
A drill?
Yes, I make hand-carved wooden figurines.
Ooh, a gorilla!
That's really well done!
Anyway, one of the girls I live with is suffering
from a hangover. So please try to keep it down?
Yeah. I'll try.
You're the loud one!
No, I'm pretty sure that's you!
Or it's you both!
This from the guy who has to be the loudest in the room?
What's going on out here?
His drilling is way too loud!
The death metal's too loud!
That creepy noise is too loud!
All I'm doing is cooking!
Huh?
At the moment, all three of you are too loud.
We're sorry, Tohru.
Why do humans always make the same
mistakes over and over? They're beyond help.
I'll kill them.
Excuse me. If I could have a word, please?
Hmm?
The problem we're all having is that everyone else manages
to be loud precisely when we'd rather things to be quiet.
So why don't we organize all the times we don't
want to have a bunch of noise driving us insane,
and plan around it?
We'll make a schedule out of our noise preferences.
If some times don't work out, then
we can use the power of the earplug.
And you're certain this plan is acceptable?
These are creatures that haven't
learned anything since evolving from apes.
You know I'm one of those creatures, right?
Mm.
It's not a big deal.
I wouldn't mind so much if I
wasn't dying in hangover hell.
Besides, it's only natural for people who are
going about their lives to annoy other people
who are simply going about theirs.
That's the definition of neighbors.
You might be too good for your own good.
No, I'm not.
I wouldn't like things if they were too quiet either.
I'm gonna take a nap real quick.
Of course.
Do you consider me to be too loud?
There are times when I feel like you are, yeah.
Does it, um, annoy...?
Hmm. Kinda difficult to give a
precise answer to that question.
However...
For what it's worth, this life's fine. Good enough for me.
I'm gonna sleep now.
Right. Then I will, too.
You're being too loud!
What should I do about this?
I don't like slowing down so I can be considerate
of management's inability to drink like me.
Straight to the point as always.
Hmm... You should create an excuse not to go.
An excuse?
We're having a party?
Yeah.
I was talking to Takiya about doing something here.
I need an excuse to get out of
my job's flower viewing thing.
You invited that man to our home?
Oh, stop making that face.
He's a nice guy. Give him a chance. Please?
I suppose so,
but I'm only putting up with him for you.
How mature.
In return, can I invite some of my friends, too?
Friends like who? People from the shopping district?
No, like dragons.
Huh?
Don't worry. They're all
extraordinarily well-behaved dragons.
Ugh. Why isn't that comforting?
I'm here.
Welcome back home!
Surprise. I'm here, too!
Oh, hi. Welcome. Come in.
Funny how I don't feel very welcome.
Now, you must be Kanna. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I like your goth-loli thing.
Hmm.
Where are your friends, Tohru?
They should be here soon.
Coming!
If you'll give me one moment, please.
Fafnir, no! Make yourself look
like the picture I sent to you!
Good grief.
I hate this and everything it stands for. Kill me.
I'm already dead inside.
Miss Kobayashi, I'd like you to meet Fafnir.
Hello, Fafnir, it's a pleasure to meet you.
That is what's known as a polite social greeting.
Polite social greeting?
It's a magical set of words that helps even the
shyest of people introduce themselves with confidence.
Tohru, I have a feeling your
friend might be hostile towards me.
That makes sense. He does have
a slight dislike for humans.
We're talking about an ancient cursed dragon who's
been guarding his treasure in a cave for, like, ever.
You mean Hobbit style?
Hm? There're more?
This one's the last.
Hey, Tohru.
Hi, there! It's been way too long!
Miss Kobayashi, this is Quetzalcoatl.
So cool to meet you. Please, call me Lucoa.
I'm gonna assume all dragons look this unrealistic.
Huh?
Oh, never mind.
It's cool or whatever to meet you, too.
Hmm? Everything chill?
Yeah, but...
Did you walk here wearing that "ensemble"?
Of course I did.
Doesn't really leave a whole
lot to the imagination, does it?
You wanna give it a try?
Now, when you get a hit, be sure to move back a little.
Just like that.
Oh, you can't attack when he's doing that move.
Almost there.
Nice work.
Hey, you killed him!
Ignore that treasure chest if you know what's good for ya.
Those things are called mimics.
Sucks. You died.
He's completely hooked, now.
It's great to see Tohru smiling;
She's not normally the type.
Hmm?
I assume that's thanks to you.
Doubtful. I'm just a normal human being.
Could be what she needed since
she's never had anything normal before.
Her friends are the same way.
You know, Lucoa. To be honest,
I'm grateful to Tohru, as well.
Truth is... I didn't use to smile very much myself.
I'd never admit that to her, though.
The food's ready, everyone!
Yay!
Watch out for her tail. Can I get you anything to drink?
Drink? Yes, thank you.
But, no offense, I'll need to check it for curses.
Curses?
Oh, yeah, forever ago, Lucoa,
who was still a goddess at the time,
had some major drama go down thanks
to being forced to drink some alcohol
an ally of hers cursed, which made
her get all sloppy with her sister.
Will you please stop talking?
I'm starting to get that a dragon's past is never good.
For the last time!
When it comes to fancy butler men,
I say give me middle-aged or give me death!
The young, handsome, and devilish
butler has been taking the world
by storm, and say what you will,
but he's here to stay, sister!
Stop messing me up.
She's entirely different when she's drunk.
Yeah.
Hey, you! You totally wanna be a maid, don't you?
Uhhhh...
You do, too!
I thought I already was one.
I've told you before, that's basic cosplay!
If you don't like the truth, then take it off!
Why?!
Fafnir!
We must avert our eyes to preserve Tohru's dignity!
Please, don't look!
Stop it!
Let go! Grr! I can't see!
Take it off!
I love how no one can not move their body to that.
Fafnir, remember to ignore that treasure chest.
Aw. It's a mimic.
No, don't go to that one either.
That was a mimic, too.
Why do you instinctively go after all the treasure?
It's my nature.