Kobayashi?
Here.
A bento lunch?
Mm-hmm. It's for next week.
I've got a field trip.
Oh!
Make one!
Okay. What kind of food do you prefer?
Don't worry about that, Miss Kobayashi.
I can take care of it.
Domestic creativity is kinda my thing!
Oh? Is that so?
Um, yeah. I'm only the best there ever was!
That's funny, because I'm even better than the best.
Well, I'm better than "even better than the best."
Sure.
According to... you.
Care to prove your so-called
betterness, or are you scared?
Careful there, Tohru.
You're good, but you're not that good.
Uh-oh. An inciting incident.
It's on!
Ready to lose?
Three rounds!
Bento Lunch Competition!
Of course you guys would make a game show set for this.
You'll each make three dishes:
A salad, a main course, and a dessert.
Use all your skills. Entertain me!
What is your character even supposed to be anymore?
Ingredients are up to you.
But remember to stay within the budget as you compete.
We don't wanna strain Miss Kobayashi's wallet, do we?
Hey!
Ready?
Begin!
They both really want to win this.
Who knew Kobayashi cared?
Finished!
First dish. Complete!
Let's see.
Contestant Kobayashi appears
to be serving cherry tomatoes.
Did you just throw the match?
You can't possibly expect to
beat a seafood and paprika Caesar.
I mean, there's no comparison.
Agreed. There's no need to compare.
The winner of the salad round is...
...Kobayashi.
What?! How'd I lose?!
I can't accept this!
How could my salad extravaganza lose to two tomatoes?
Calm down. Allow me to explain your first round failure.
Now, then.
The problem, Contestant Tohru,
is that you were not prepared
because you didn't bother to find
out the definition of a bento lunch.
There was limited space.
And you made too much!
That's all right.
I'll win next!
Tohru wins.
Bacon and eggs can't lose!
Hamburger's better, though.
But bacon and eggs are a delicious staple!
Hamburger's better.
No, it's not...
Although, when I was a kid...
...I always asked my parents to make burgers...
Last round is dessert.
Something in a cup, or a fruit would work.
You are to bring one item that has not been cooked.
'Kay.
Tohru.
This is rather unusual.
You and Kobayashi don't normally fight.
No, we don't.
Not ever.
So why...?
I'm heading off.
Be careful.
This is deplorable.
What do you mean?
I love seeing Tohru like this.
It's refreshing!
It's the final round, oh, what am I going to get?
Hold on.
I know!
Of course. It's perfect!
You realize this fight only happened
because you've grown so close to each other.
I mean, you're fighting but
you're not, like, fighting-fighting.
Either way, it's not a big deal.
She may be a dragon maid. But she can be my friend, too.
Excuse me.
You cannot honestly believe
that you and a dragon are equals...
...human?
That's at least how Tohru and I both feel about it.
Probably why we fought today, too.
Good grief. Why is Tohru not back yet?
Close enough to fight.
This is disgusting.
I'm back!
Oh! Hi, Miss Kobayashi.
You're late!
I'm sorry.
I'm so not gonna lose, now!
Really?
Because I'm not gonna lose either.
Wait. My shoes...
Third round complete!
What's that thing?
Why? Would you like to try some?
Wow!
That's so good!
What is it? Where do they sell it?
Um... The shopping district, I guess?
Did she just do what I think she did?
Yep.
It's a fruit?
No way. I've never seen this before.
It's official!
You can tell her that I won now!
Items from the other world are against the rules.
Oopsie...
Tohru!
Whew, that was awesome. Thanks.
Sure!
Just to be clear, your food's
always been delicious, Tohru.
Jeez, are you trying to flatter me?
Oh, yeah. We've got dessert!
What's wrong, Tohru?
Who would've thought I'd find
you hiding out here of all places...
...Tohru!
Our home...
Have you forgotten all of our laws?!
Dragons disrupt the order of this world and are forbidden!
You are to return with me!
I see you're as boring and persistent as ever.
Surprise. I'm not going back.
Lady Tohru and Lady Elma are on very bad terms.
Yeah?
They're like cats and dogs.
Oh! Did you learn that idiom at school?
Good girl.
If you asked me, they look like
they're about to explode any second.
You think they'll be okay?
I can't say.
Last time they fought, three islands disappeared.
That's awful!
Our power may be considered equal by some...
...but this time, I plan on settling the score!
Her stomach just growled like no big whoop.
I'd be mortified, but dragons don't care about that stuff.
After all...
Or maybe not. She looks embarrassed.
Shut up, human! You are being very distracting right now!
Well, you've got quite the attitude on ya
considering you just destroyed my home.
Maybe you should follow the laws in
this world before you try protecting it.
Even Tohru wouldn't do something like this.
Sorry...
Prob'ly.
I'm sorry!
Wait. Why do I always wind up doing the apologizing?!
That says a lot.
Hey. She doesn't seem like a bad person,
so why don't you all get along?
Because we're from different factions.
Not all dragons are united in thought.
There's the harmony faction that values law and order,
the chaos faction that yearns for chaos and destruction,
and the spectating faction that doesn't
work with either group or even each other.
Wow.
Elma belongs to the harmony faction.
I'm with chaos, obviously.
So we oppose each other.
Hold up, you're one of the villains?
No, no, that is not true.
I am a good dragon, and I'm on my
very best behavior in this world.
That sounded a bit forced.
Sorry to interrupt!
But I'm taking you home, Tohru! By force, if I must.
Yeah? Try it!
I'll eliminate you from this world
and leave no trace of your filth behind!
Take it somewhere else!
I've prepared another dimension. We can finish this there.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just surprised to see the
fiendish Tohru listening to a human.
What in this world happened?
Hurry up!
Hey! You cheated!
Who, me? No, I simply respected order like she wanted.
It was a peaceful resolution.
Now then, would you like me to fix
what she so carelessly destroyed?
By the way, where'd you send her?
The field Kanna and I played in that one time.
Oh man. Where am I?
How dare you trick me?!
You actually came back here?
I can't believe you sent me to another continent!
Can we stop this? I'm not gonna do anything.
I'll be happy as long as I can
quietly be a maid in this world.
Hey, Tohru? What's going on?
The freak decided to come back.
Oh, yeah, I'm the freak?!
You're planning to take over this world, just admit it!
You're wrong.
Shut your mouth! No more excuses!
Oh, you poor thing...
You haven't had any food to eat since yesterday, have you?
I can't...
I'm not from this world... so
I'm not allowed to interfere.
Oh.
Here, something like this should be all right, yeah?
Come on. Try some. It's cream bread.
Thank you...
I'll kindly take you up on the offer.
If only to restore my strength.
What's this?
It's melting in my mouth!
I think I just ate heaven!
All right. I'm energized now!
Time for us to have that rematch, Tohru!
Or you could go away.
If you do, I'll let you have all of these.
Sorry for the intrusion!
Too big, way too big...
I'm being crushed...
Who's this?
I'll be working with you starting today.
My name is Elma Joui.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
No way!
What the heck is going on? Why are you here?
I could ask you the same question, human.
This is my work, so I get to ask stuff.
This cannot be just a coincidence, can it?
I'm investigating... It's cultural standard research.
I wanna see if beings from other
worlds can really integrate successfully.
That makes sense.
She did say you were with the harmony faction.
Wait, can you even do this job?
You know you can't use magic.
Don't be silly!
Trust me. I can do human labor better than any human.
You just watch and learn!
What the heck is this...?
I don't understand any of it.
What are these bizarre boxes?
And what is everyone doing with them?
Ooh! I think I did something!
Yeah. Try this.
Yep. Then, you push this.
Apologies, human.
You do some pretty difficult work.
But I've taken the time to memorize Romanized
character input and that kind of nonsense,
so I won't fall behind anymore!
Hope not.
I do have a question.
When will I receive compensation for today's labor?
Oh. That's, uh, about a month from now.
Do you mean to tell me I won't receive my pay tomorrow?
No. We total out at the end of the month,
and today's the first, so it'll be a while yet.
Then what do I do for rent and food in the meantime?
Well, if you commute from the other world, I...
Let me guess, you can't go back.
Right...
I don't possess enough power to open the
gate between worlds at will like Tohru can.
I thought your power was equal to Tohru's.
It is. I'm just as strong as her, but in a different way.
Wait here.
I know you've got a lot on your plate, but hang in there.
If you're gonna be working with
me, I'll teach you as much as I can.
Don't want ya making my life harder.
You have my gratitude.
That's pretty hot, so be careful.
Later!
Yummy!
I probably should keep quiet about meeting Elma today.
Hey, guys. I'm home!
Welcome back!
Guess what we're having for dinner...
What're you doing?
There's a strange smell on you.
Is it a dog?
No, it's a dragon!
Are you secretly cheating on me?
Whatever. Look, so, today at work...
Wait, is it an office romance?!
Congrats. You've picked up another weird phrase.
Can't breathe... I can't breathe...
Miss Kobayashi!
Thanks for your help today!
You're doing great.
You've learned a lot about PC operation, huh?
Impressive.
I'm all over this!
Yep. I'm gonna prove myself to you.
Good, because you've still got a ways to go.
Oh, Miss Kobayashi, let's grab
some sweet chestnuts on the way home!
They're so yummy!
Sure, whatever.
Why, you...
It's been a while since my last day off.
Ugh, I wanna do nothing.
Morning! Please excuse me!
I'll clean everything so you can enjoy
your day off in a clean room, Miss Kobayashi!
Does that sound good to you?
Yeah, I mean, I guess.
It's not that I'm not grateful, but...
Hey! What are you doing?!
What do you think?
When I get serious, I can make a room spotless!
Except for the sparkling, of course.
This room's never been so clean!
It's brand new, as if Shiva passed through!
What about my furniture?
A space for relaxation doesn't need any of that nonsense!
Please enjoy sleeping to your heart's
content in this spacious and relaxing room!
As if I could!
Put it back the way it was!
I swear...
Kobayashi.
I'm really hungry.
Yeah, I could eat, too. Let's have breakfast, okay?
Hold it right there!
I'm in charge of breakfast, be it a
full course meal or an imperial feast!
Oh! Would you like me to slaughter a cow?
I think I'd prefer to have something light.
Yes! I understand!
Ta-dah! Sandwiches!
Oh!
They look good.
Wait. This meat...
Tohru.
Show me your butt, now!
You mean you want me to satisfy
your lust, and not your appetite?
Are you dumb?
Yes...
I knew it!
The tail again?
What's going on?
What do you mean?
You're just unusually gung-ho.
You really can't tell what's wrong?
I can't. You're spinning your wheels, though.
It's like you reverted to how
you were when you first came to me.
Oh. Coming!
No, it's fine. I'll get it.
Hello?
Good morning, Miss Kobayashi! How are you?
Elma?
What are you here for?
Well. You know I appreciate
how you're always helping me out,
so I decided to bring you something to say thanks.
What's this?
A protective charm.
It turned out well, too.
Whaaat? You made this? So cool. Thanks!
Oh. I get it, now.
Tohru!
Today, I'm taking you back!
Be gone, Elma!
Miss Kobayashi.
I know that I can be really selfish.
So, I try to control myself and put up with it.
But...
I feel like you're being mean.
I work hard, too...
All I want is a lot of praise.
And maybe to have you pet my head a little bit...
Look, Tohru.
I'm not used to being wanted
or even thought that much about.
This has never happened to me before.
I don't have a clue what to do about it.
Human relationships...
I dunno. I've always found them to be super confusing.
I have a tendency to put distance
between me and other people.
I've had friends before.
But I never let them get too close.
So here.
I mean, um...
I can't make it any clearer than this, okay?
Take the hint, please.
Yes, I'll take the hint...
Oh, right. I can make you a protective charm, too.
Then, you'll also gain the protection of evil gods!
It'll be great!
No, thanks.
Why're you so handsy, Shouta, baby?
Bad demon!
Tohru! You're too dangerous!
You know that yourself!
Elma, you're too... Uh...
What?
For now, please put down the cream bread you're holding.
How come? They're so yummy!
I don't care.