[AMAIMON]
UNBELIEVABLE POWER!
JUST LIKE FATHER'S.
[ROARING]
KUCHEN KUCKUCKS UHR!
- [CHIMING]
- [CUCKOOS]
HUH?
[CUCKOOS]
[AMAIMON SCREAMING]
[SHOUTING]
[MEPHISTO]
MY, MY.
YOU'RE SUCH A HANDFUL,
LITTLE BROTHER.
♪ [MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[EXPLOSIONS RUMBLING]
[ALL PANTING]
WHAT THE HECK'S
GOING ON OVER THERE?
OH, GOD, THE BLUE FLAMES.
- OH, NO.
- RIN.
[AMAIMON GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING]
HIS POWER IS EVEN GREATER
THAN I THOUGHT.
NOT EVEN THE KOMA SWORD
CAN CONTAIN IT NOW.
[SHOUTING, GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING]
NO, RIN.
RIN!
SHIEMI!
- [GROWLING]
- [GASPS]
STAY BACK!
WE GOT THIS.
[GROWLING]
[SNARLING]
RIN! RIN!
[GASPS]
SHI... EMI.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
RIN!
[SIGHS]
AH, SO BLUE.
[GASPING]
AS BLUE AS IT WAS
THAT NIGHT, NO?
HUH?
WHO'S THAT?
OH, GREAT.
GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE.
ARTHUR AUGUSTE ANGEL,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
I'M A SENIOR EXORCIST
FIRST CLASS
FROM VATICAN HEADQUARTERS.
ARTHUR AUGUSTE ANGEL?
HE GOT PROMOTED
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
HE'S THE NEW PALADIN.
HUH? THE PALADIN?
THAT IS CORRECT.
I AM YOUR SUPERVISOR NOW, SHURA.
HMPH!
NOW THEN.
CARE TO EXPLAIN
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WEREN'T YOU ASSIGNED
TO INVESTIGATE
A POSSIBLE CONSPIRACY?
ONE BETWEEN THE LATE
SHIRO FUJIMOTO...
AND THE JAPAN BRANCH PRECEPT,
MEPHISTO PHELES?
AM I CORRECT?
YEAH, WELL, I'M NOT
THE ONLY SPY YOU GOT
STASHED HERE, AM I?
TOO TRUE.
AND THAT BRINGS US TO THE OTHER
CRUCIAL TASK YOU WERE ASSIGNED.
IF YOU DISCOVER THE PLOT HAD
ANYTHING TO DO WITH SATAN,
YOU WERE TO ELIMINATE IT
AT ONCE.
[BOTH GRUNT]
SHURA, WOULDN'T YOU SAY...
THIS BLUE-FLAMED SPEWING BEAST
HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH SATAN?
YOU'RE AS PERCEPTIVE AS ALWAYS,
AREN'T YOU?
- MEPHISTO.
- LONG TIME NO SEE, ANGEL.
I HEARD THROUGH THE GRAPEVINE
YOU'VE BEEN APPOINTED
TO THE RANK OF PALADIN.
YOU HAVE MY CONGRATULATIONS,
GOOD SIR.
SO YOU'VE SHOWN YOUR TAIL.
REPORTS OF YOUR TREACHERY
HAVE REACHED THE EARS
OF THE THREE SAGES,
THE GRIGORI, AND THIS IS
THE PROOF THEY NEED
TO SEAL YOUR FATE.
ACTUALLY, A GENTLEMAN
NEVER SHOWS HIS TAIL.
SUCH ACCUSATIONS
ARE QUITE RUDE, YOU KNOW.
[CHUCKLES]
INDEED.
CALIBAN, LEND ME YOUR POWER.
OOH, GLADLY, ARTHUR.
BY ORDER OF THE GRIGORI,
ADVISERS OF THE TRUE CROSS,
- [GASPS]
- I SHALL EXECUTE
THE SPAWN OF SATAN.
[SHOUTS]
RIN!
KIRIGAKURE SWORD TECHNIQUE,
SNAKE BELLY!
SNAKE FANG!
- [GASPS]
- WHY DO YOU PROTECT HIM?
ARE YOU IN LEAGUE
WITH MEPHISTO?
- YEAH, LIKE HELL I AM.
- FUJIMOTO WANTED YOU TO TEACH
THE BOY SWORDSMANSHIP.
SURELY YOU DON'T INTEND
TO FULFILL THE DYING WISH...
OF THE MOST UNFIT PALADIN
IN HISTORY.
LIKE I SAID,
YOU BALD-ASS BASTARD--
[LAUGHS]
YOUR HUMOR DEFIES LOGIC.
DO I LOOK BALD TO YOU?
REGARDLESS, THE GRIGORI'S
ORDERS ARE ABSOLUTE.
EVEN FOR SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
YES.
UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
THAT WAS THE GRIGORI
JUST NOW.
MEPHISTO PHELES,
YOU ARE HEREBY ORDERED...
TO REPORT TO THEM IMMEDIATELY
FOR A DISCIPLINARY HEARING.
REALLY? OH, GOODY.
I CAN'T WAIT.
SHURA, YOU'RE A WITNESS,
SO IF YOU DON'T MIND,
YOU'RE COMING ALONG WITH ME.
THE SPAWN OF SATAN COMES TOO.
I'LL NEED HIM AS EVIDENCE.
EXCUSE ME.
I'D LIKE TO COME TOO.
[MEPHISTO] I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU SHOULD STAY HERE
AND LOOK AFTER YOUR STUDENTS.
LIKE A GOOD TEACHER.
HIS FLAMES CAN'T BE SUPPRESSED
ANY LONGER...
NOW THAT HIS SWORD IS DAMAGED.
[GASPS]
WELL, ANGEL,
SHALL WE GO?
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[MAN]
THE COURT WILL NOW HEAR
THE CASE OF MEPHISTO PHELES,
PRECEPT OF THE JAPAN BRANCH
OF THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
I, TIMOTHÉ TIMOWAN,
CHIEF JUSTICE OF THE ORDER,
AND ARTHUR AUGUSTE ANGEL,
THE CURRENT PALADIN,
WILL CARRY OUT
THE INTERROGATION.
PRESIDING ARE THE GRIGORI,
ADVISERS TO THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
SIR PHELES,
LET'S GET STRAIGHT
TO THE POINT.
IS THIS CREATURE
I SEE BEFORE ME
THE SON OF SATAN?
THAT HE IS, YOUR HONOR.
I SIMPLY CAN'T HIDE THE TRUTH
ANY LONGER.
FIFTEEN YEARS AGO
MY BROTHER RIN WAS BORN.
HIS MOTHER WAS HUMAN.
SATAN WAS HIS FATHER.
AS A RESULT, HE'S INHERITED
THE POWER
OF SATAN'S BLUE FLAMES.
[ALL GASP]
UM, I DON'T MEAN TO PRY,
BUT YOU AND HE ARE TWINS.
SO DOES THAT MEAN
YOU HAVE THAT POWER TOO?
NO. I DIDN'T INHERIT
THE BLUE FLAMES.
I HAVE TO GET EXAMINED
FOR IT EVERY DAY THOUGH.
AS FAR AS I KNOW,
I'M STILL HUMAN.
[WOMAN] TO CLARIFY, YURI EGIN,
JUNIOR EXORCIST SECOND CLASS,
GAVE BIRTH TO SATAN'S SON.
BUT THE REPORT STATES
THAT FUJIMOTO KILLED HIM
WITH THE KOMA SWORD.
AND NOW YOU'RE SAYING
THAT REPORT WAS FALSE?
YES. THE FACT IS
TWO CHILDREN WERE BORN,
BUT ONLY ONE
INHERITED THE POWER OF SATAN.
AND THAT CHILD
IS THE ONE BEFORE YOU NOW.
HE WOULD'VE TURNED
INTO A DEMON,
SO I SEALED THE SOURCE
OF HIS POWER,
HIS DEMONIC HEART,
WITHIN THE KOMA SWORD.
EVENTUALLY, HIS POWER
BECAME TOO GREAT
FOR THE KOMA SWORD TO CONTAIN.
IT AWOKE INSIDE HIM
ABOUT THREE MONTHS AGO.
THREE MONTHS AGO?
AND UNTIL THAT DAY,
RIN GREW UP NOT KNOWING
THE TRUTH ABOUT HIMSELF.
[THINKING]
BUT THAT'S WHEN--
DON'T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS.
I'M NOT A DEMON.
GOT IT?
THAT'S WHY HE WAS ANGRY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
GONNA DO TO RIN?
DEPENDING ON THE VERDICT,
THEY COULD DECIDE
TO EXECUTE HIM.
REALLY?
ONCE HE'S CONSUMED
BY THE POWER OF THE FLAMES,
HE'LL TRANSFORM INTO A DEMON.
IF THAT HAPPENS,
HE CAN'T BE ALLOWED
TO LIVE IN THIS WORLD ANYMORE.
BUT, YUKI, YOU SOUND
LIKE YOU DON'T EVEN CARE
IF RIN DIES.
I NEVER SAID THAT!
I DIDN'T.
I JUST DON'T WANT HIM
TO SUFFER ANYMORE.
EVEN IF RIN WANTS TO,
HE CAN'T GO BACK TO LIVING
A NORMAL HUMAN LIFE.
ESPECIALLY NOW...
THAT HIS SWORD'S
CRACKED.
WHAT? KURIKARA'S BLADE
IS CRACKED?
WHAT DID YOU JUST CALL IT?
HUH?
I'VE ALWAYS CALLED THIS
THE KOMA SWORD,
BUT YOU CALLED IT
KURIKARA.
HOW DO YOU
EVEN KNOW THAT?
KURIKARA.
IT'S THE SWORD'S REAL NAME.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE
CALLED IT BACK WHEN IT WAS ONE
OF MY TEMPLE'S TREASURES.
[GASPS]
BON, DO YOU THINK
IF WE BROUGHT IT
TO THE YOSHIKUNIS,
THEY MIGHT BE ABLE
TO DO SOMETHING?
YOSHIKUNIS?
THE FAMILY OF SWORDSMITHS
WHO FORGED KURIKARA.
THERE'S ONLY ONE
OF THEM LEFT NOW.
DO YOU THINK
THEY MIGHT BE ABLE
TO FIX IT?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
[ALL]
HUH?
THAT'S CRAZY.
DO YOU GUYS EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
AREN'T YOU SCARED?
FIX THE SWORD?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHY ON EARTH WOULD ANYONE
WANT TO DO THAT?
[SHIEMI]
BECAUSE RIN IS OUR--
[MIWA] HE'S THE SON OF SATAN!
I KNOW HOW YOU ALL MUST FEEL.
I UNDERSTAND WHY.
BUT PLEASE, IF THERE'S A WAY
TO SAVE MY BROTHER,
I NEED YOUR HELP.
PLEASE.
- CUT IT OUT.
- SUGURO.
[WOMAN]
SIR PHELES,
YOU ADMIT TO HAVING
SHIRO FUJIMOTO
RAISE THE BOY IN SECRET.
MY QUESTION
TO YOU IS, WHY?
EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
TO FIGHT SATAN.
I WAS TURNING HIM INTO A WEAPON
FOR THE ORDER.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
[PEOPLE GASPING]
YOU'D USE THAT BOY
TO FIGHT SATAN?
[WOMAN]
THAT'S MONSTROUS!
HE'S LYING!
I ADVISE THE COURT
TO THINK TWICE
BEFORE BELIEVING THIS SWINDLER.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
SURELY YOU HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
WHAT PHELES IS.
LIES ARE THE STOCK AND TRADE
OF HIS KIND.
[SIGHS]
OKAY, LET'S GET GOING.
COME ON, TAKE US
TO THIS YOSHIKUNI PERSON.
HELLO? YOU GUYS
ARE THE ONLY ONES
WHO KNOW HOW TO GET THERE.
KAMIKI.
WHATEVER.
I'M TIRED OF LISTENING
TO EVERYONE TALKING
AND NOT DOING ANYTHING.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
WELL, BON?
[SIGHS]
[SHIMA]
ONE SECOND,
WE'RE IN KYOTO.
THIS KEY CAN TRANSPORT US
TO ANY CITY INSTANTLY...
AS LONG AS IT HAS
A RELIGIOUS SITE.
LEAD THE WAY.
MM.
YEAH.
[HAMMERING]
[SIGHS]
HMM?
RYUGI!
[GRUNTS]
HEY!
- OKAY.
- [GIGGLING]
[GROANING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CHATTERING]
[GASPS]
HEY, GUYS?
[GRUNTS]
[SHOUTING]
[SCREAMING]
[WOMAN]
NO ONE ARGUES THE FACT...
THAT WE VIEW DEMONS
AS OUR ENEMY.
HOWEVER, WE'VE LEARNED MUCH
FROM THEM OVER THE CENTURIES.
THE BENEFITS OF THIS KNOWLEDGE
CAN BE SEEN IN THE
COUNTERMEASURES WE'VE DEVELOPED.
EVEN SO, NONE OF THAT CAN EVEN
BEGIN TO DISPEL THE SUSPICIONS
OF TREACHERY BY SIR PHELES.
AND YET HE HAS COOPERATED
WITH THE ORDER FOR 200 YEARS.
SURELY THAT IS REASON
ENOUGH TO TRUST HIM.
[ANGEL]
THIS DEMON CONSPIRED
WITH SHIRO FUJIMOTO...
TO RAISE THE SON OF SATAN.
THAT FACT IS INDISPUTABLE.
[SUGURO]
SHE'S 11TH GENERATION YOSHIKUNI.
DESCENDED
FROM THE SWORDSMITH
WHO FORGED KURIKARA.
A FEMALE SWORDSMITH?
THAT SHOULDN'T BE
SO SURPRISING.
WHY, DURING THE MID-EDO PERIOD,
THERE WAS A MASTER SWORDSMITH
KNOWN AS LADY KUNISHIGE.
THEIR NAMES MIGHT NOT BE
IN THE HISTORY BOOKS, BUT I KNOW
THERE WERE LOTS MORE LIKE HER.
THE LADY REALLY KNOWS
HER STUFF.
HELL, THIS CHICK'S GONNA BE
THE NEXT ONE TO LEAVE HER MARK
ON THE WORLD.
WHO ARE YOU CALLING "CHICK,"
YOU POSEUR?
[GROANS]
WATCH IT!
[CHUCKLES]
BON'S BEEN PUT
IN HIS PLACE.
MY FATHER AND I GO
TO RYUGI'S TEMPLE
TO CLEAN STUFF,
SO WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
SINCE WE WERE LITTLE KIDS.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HIM.
HE WAS SO CUTE.
HE WAS ALWAYS TRYING
TO CUDDLE WITH ME AND STUFF.
[GASPS]
COME ON, YOU DID.
DON'T DENY IT.
- WOULD YOU STOP IT?
- HE WANTED TO MARRY ME.
HE EVEN MADE AN ENGAGEMENT RING
FOR ME OUT OF LOTUS FLOWERS.
- GEEZ, CUT IT OUT!
- [LAUGHING]
HE WAS ALL,
"PLEASE, MARRY ME.
PLEASE. PLEASE."
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
A LOT OF WORK,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
BUT IT'S NOT IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU CAN REALLY FIX IT?
MAYBE.
IN ORDER TO FORGE
A JAPANESE SWORD,
YOU NEED IRON SAND
SMELTED IN A FURNACE AT
A SPECIFIC TEMPERATURE.
THE PROCESS IS
A LITTLE DIFFERENT
FOR DEMON SWORDS THOUGH.
YOU HAVE TO INFUSE
THE IRON SAND WITH SPIRITUAL
POWER THROUGH A RITUAL.
BUT HERE'S THE PROBLEM--
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE...
WHO REMEMBERS HOW TO PERFORM
THAT RITUAL ANYMORE.
AND THERE ARE NO RECORDS
OF IT LEFT ANYWHERE?
HMM-MM. IT'S NOT POSSIBLE
TO MAKE A DEMON SWORD
ANY OTHER WAY.
I WISH I KNEW ANOTHER.
[SIGHS]
SO WE CAME HERE FOR NOTHING?
OKAY, WE DON'T KNOW THE RITUAL,
BUT WHAT IF YOU HAD IRON SAND
THAT HAD ALREADY BEEN BLESSED?
I GUESS IF I GOT
MY HANDS ON SOME.
BUT WHERE WOULD WE FIND
SOMETHING LIKE THAT NOW?
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD USE
THOSE TEMPLE NAILS?
[YOSHIKUNI]
WHAT TEMPLE NAILS?
[SUGURO]
THERE USED TO BE A TOWER
AS OLD AS OUR TEMPLE.
WHEN THE BLUE NIGHT HAPPENED,
IT BURNED DOWN.
NOTHING WAS LEFT EXCEPT A BUNCH
OF THICK TEMPLE NAILS.
THEY TURNED OUT TO BE PRETTY
VALUABLE, SO WE DECIDED TO KEEP
THEM AT OUR SISTER TEMPLE.
ANYWAY, LONG STORY SHORT,
THOSE NAILS WERE MADE
BY THE YOSHIKUNIS, RIGHT?
SO THERE'S A CHANCE THEY WERE
MADE WITH THE SAME IRON SAND
USED FOR THE SWORD.
[YOSHIKUNI] WELL, MAYBE
KURIKARA AND THE NAILS WERE
MADE FROM THE SAME STUFF.
[YUKIO]
THEN IF WE CAN GET OUR HANDS
ON THOSE TEMPLE NAILS--
[YOSHIKUNI]
I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO FIX THE SWORD.
[SHIMA]
ANYBODY HOME?
HELLO?
THAT'S WEIRD.
ARE THEY AT LUNCH?
HMM.
OH, WELL.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK AROUND.
I'M GONNA CHECK
THE MAIN HALL.
MIND IF I GO
WITH YOU?
LOOKS LIKE NOBODY'S HOME.
I'M GONNA GO OUT BACK
AND CHECK THE CHARNEL HOUSE.
YOU WAIT HERE FOR ME,
OKAY, TEACH?
[CICADAS BUZZING]
[SHIMA]
HELLO?
IS ANYONE AROUND?
HEY, ANYONE?
HELLO?
[GASPS]
[SHIEMI]
OVER THERE!
OH, PLEASE TELL ME
THAT GUY ISN'T DEAD.
HE'S OKAY.
HE'S JUST UNCONSCIOUS, IS ALL.
[GASPS]
LOOK! SO ARE THEY.
[MALE VOICE]
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU WANT TO KILL SATAN,
DON'T YOU?
[GASPS]
[FEMALE VOICE]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY ARE YOU TRYING SO HARD
TO SAVE A DEMON?
DON'T LIE.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE FEELING.
YOU KNOW NOTHING.
BE HONEST WITH YOURSELF.
HE IS THE SON OF SATAN
AFTER ALL.
THE WORLD WOULD BE
BETTER OFF WITHOUT HIM.
ISN'T THAT HOW YOU FEEL?
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO SAVE
THE SON OF SATAN?
WHY? BECAUSE YOU HAPPEN
TO BE RELATED BY BLOOD?
ARE YOU A DEMON?
YOU KNOW I AM NOT THE ONE
YOU HAVE TO DEFEAT.
DEEP IN YOUR HEART,
YOU KNOW WHO YOU FEAR THE MOST--
YOUR BROTHER.
AS LONG AS HE LIVES,
YOU WILL ALWAYS LIVE
IN FEAR OF HIS POWER.
OF HIM.
I ASK AGAIN--
WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO SAVE HIM?
WHAT REASON IS THERE
FOR SAVING THE SON OF SATAN?
REASON.
DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR TEMPLE BECAUSE OF SATAN?
WHY THEN SHOULD YOU SAVE
HIS SON?
[EXHALES]
[GASPS]
WHY MAKE YOUR LIFE HARDER?
ALL YOU NEED DO
IS TURN YOUR BACK.
LET THE ORDER
GET RID OF YOUR BROTHER,
AND THEN YOU CAN LIVE
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
WITHOUT FEAR.
- HEY, TEACH!
- SHIMA.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
- [GUN COCKS]
- YOU'RE WRONG.
MY BROTHER ISN'T THE ONE
I'M AFRAID OF.
I'M SCARED
I WON'T BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO PROTECT HIM WHEN HE NEEDS ME.
I SWORE I'D BECOME
A STRONGER PERSON JUST SO
I COULD PROTECT MY BROTHER.
I SWORE I'D PROTECT HIM.
[SIGHS, PANTS]
BEGONE, DEMON!
SUGURO!
[GASPS]
[GROWLS]
YOU WANT A REASON?
I GOT ONE FOR YA.
IN THE MIDDLE OF CLASS,
HE TELLS ME HE WANTS TO BE
AN EXORCIST...
SO HE CAN KICK SATAN'S ASS,
AND HE'S THE FRIGGIN' SON
OF SATAN.
I NEVER HEARD ANYTHING
SO TWISTED IN MY LIFE.
SO IF HE DIES
BEFORE I CAN ASK HIM
WHAT HE MEANT,
I'LL BE PISSED!
[CHANTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[SIGHS, PANTS]
[SUGURO]
THE HEAD PRIEST IS SAFE.
GOOD. I'M GLAD.
THE DEMON WE CONFRONTED,
IT WAS MARA, WASN'T IT?
YES. MARA TRIED
TO DISTRACT SIDDHARTHA...
WHILE HE WAS MEDITATING
TO REACH ENLIGHTENMENT.
PREYING ON A PERSON'S DOUBTS
AND WEAKNESSES, HUH? TYPICAL.
I REMEMBER HEARING
ABOUT DEMONS LIKE MARA...
AND HOW THEY POSSESS
THE BUDDHIST STATUES
IN OLD TEMPLES.
I BROUGHT THE TEMPLE NAILS
YOU ASKED FOR.
GREAT. THANK YOU.
HE PLANNED TO BETRAY THE ORDER
AND DESTROY IT FROM WITHIN.
THERE CAN BE NO DOUBT
ABOUT MEPHISTO'S TREACHERY.
BUT EVEN SO, THE ORDER HAS NEVER
HAD A WEAPON POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO DEFEAT SATAN AND HIS ARMIES.
THE MAGNITUDE OF THIS ISSUE
IS UNPRECEDENTED.
AN ERROR IN JUDGMENT
COULD SPELL THE END
OF THE ORDER.
[THINKING]
DAMN, HOW LONG
ARE THEY GONNA KEEP YAPPING?
- [RUMBLING]
- [SHURA]
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
[CHUCKLES]
DAMN HIM.
[AMAIMON]
WHERE IS HE?
TELL ME WHERE HE IS.
I HAVEN'T LOST THE BATTLE YET.
[FEMALE GRIGORI]
AMAIMON?
HOW DID HE GET IN HERE?
- [MAN]
ANGEL!
- YES, SIR.
SIR PHELES,
ARE YOU BEHIND THIS?
YOU JEST, MILORD.
WHAT ON EARTH WOULD I HAVE
TO GAIN BY CAUSING SUCH MISCHIEF
AT MY OWN HEARING?
THAT BEING SAID, MIGHT I SUGGEST
WE TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
INSTEAD OF TALKING
ABOUT HIS POTENTIAL,
SEE FOR YOURSELVES
JUST HOW POWERFUL
THE SPAWN OF SATAN IS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[MEPHISTO]
WE ARE UNDER SIEGE, MILADY.
AND CURRENTLY THE BOY
IS THE ONLY WEAPON
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO PROTECT US.
WHO WOULD LIKE TO BET
ON WHETHER RIN OKUMURA BECOMES
THE SAVIOR OF ASSIAH...
OR HE BECOMES THE DEMON KING
OF GEHENNA?
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO SEE
THE OUTCOME
WITH YOUR VERY OWN EYES?
♪ [WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE]
MM-HMM.
RIGHT.
THIS IS GOING TO WORK.
- [GASPING]
- YEAH!
[RUMBLING]
[MEPHISTO]
NO PRESSURE, BUT THE POLLS
WILL BE CLOSING SOON.
TIME TO CAST YOUR VOTES--
YEA OR NAY.
- [YUKIO] YOU FIEND!
- [AMAIMON] I'VE COME TO
SETTLE THINGS, RIN OKUMURA.
[YUKIO]
WAKE UP!