[ MAN, OVER RADIO ]
WE HAVE AN UPDATE...
OF THIS AFTERNOON'S
HOSTAGE CRISIS
AT TRUE CROSS ACADEMY.
ALL THE STUDENTS
HAVE BEEN RESCUED.
HOWEVER, THE SUSPECT
IS STILL AT LARGE.
THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS
HAVE SEALED OFF A 20-KILOMETER
AREA AROUND THE SCHOOL.
[ MOTHER ]
SHIEMI.
[ GASPS ]
IF YOU HAVE A SEC,
DO ME A FAVOR--
BREW THAT VALERIAN FOR ME.
I'LL BE BACK
IN A BIT, OKAY?
OKAY.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
...POSSIBLE MOTIVES.
THE HOSTAGES RANGED IN AGE--
I WONDER IF EVERYONE AT SCHOOL
IS ALL RIGHT.
[ LOUD CLANG ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
THAT LOOKS BAD.
IT NEEDS TREATMENT RIGHT AWAY.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
I CAN'T MOVE HER.
WHAT DO I DO?
NEE!
NEE?
[ VOICES ]
NEE. NEE.
HUH? WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING
TO HELP ME MOVE HER?
[ DEEP VOICE ]
NEE.
HUH?
WHAT?
♪ [ MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ TRAIN HORN BLOWS ]
[ EGIN ]
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
PLEASE, HAVE A SEAT.
THEY SAY BOYS SOMETIMES TAKE
AFTER THEIR MOTHERS.
LOOKING AT YOU, I SEE
A RESEMBLANCE TO YURI.
YURI?
DIDN'T FUJIMOTO
TELL YOU ABOUT HER?
HE DIDN'T.
NOT A THING.
I SEE.
THAT IS THE ONLY PHOTOGRAPH
I HAVE OF YURI.
I KNOW THAT BEFORE HE DIED,
FUJIMOTO APPOINTED SIR PHELES
AS YOUR GUARDIAN.
WHEN I FOUND OUT
HE HAD BEEN ARRESTED BY
THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS,
I DECIDED TO TAKE ACTION.
I'D LIKE TO TAKE YOU
AND YOUR BROTHER IN.
I AM YOUR GRANDFATHER
AFTER ALL.
WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
IN KINDERGARTEN,
TEACHER ONCE MADE US DRAW
A PICTURE OF OUR MOTHER
FOR MOTHER'S DAY.
RIN DREW WHAT HE THOUGHT
SHE LOOKED LIKE.
BUT I COULDN'T
NO MATTER HOW HARD I TRIED.
I FEEL THE SAME NOW
AS I DID THEN.
FOR 15 YEARS,
YOU LIVED A LIFE
OF PAIN AND LONELINESS.
I AM SO SORRY
FOR HAVING PUT YOU
THROUGH THAT.
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I HAD NO OTHER CHOICE.
YOU SEE, I WAS IMPRISONED
THAT WHOLE TIME.
- IMPRISONED?
- FIFTEEN YEARS AGO,
I SURVIVED THE BLUE NIGHT,
BUT IN THAT INSTANT
I LOST EVERYTHING.
MY STANDING, MY HONOR,
THIS FACE OF MINE,
NOT TO MENTION
MY BELOVED DAUGHTER YURI.
SHE DIED? THEN SHE WAS KILLED
BY SATAN LIKE ALL THE OTHERS.
NO. SHE DIDN'T DIE
BY SATAN'S HANDS.
IT WAS MY JAILERS, THE VATICAN.
[ GASPS ]
ON THAT HORRIBLE DAY WHEN SATAN
DESTROYED ALL THE EXORCISTS,
THE VATICAN FOUND OUT
YURI WAS PREGNANT
WITH THE SPAWN OF SATAN.
YOU MEAN MY BROTHER AND ME.
[ EGIN ]
THE GRIGORI EXECUTED YURI
AS A WITCH.
[ CLAMORING ]
NO! THE WITCH HUNTS
HAVE BEEN OVER FOR CENTURIES.
WHY WOULD THEY CONDEMN
MY MOTHER TO DEATH LIKE THAT?
THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS
WERE TRYING TO RESTORE
THEIR AUTHORITY.
THEY USED YURI
AS THEIR SCAPEGOAT.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- [ TRAIN HORN BLARES ]
[ EGIN ]
THE ORDER OPERATES THE SAME WAY
THEY DID 600 YEARS AGO.
FOR BEING THE FATHER OF A WITCH,
I WAS THROWN INTO PRISON
AND LEFT TO ROT.
I ALMOST LOST THE WILL TO LIVE,
BUT I HAD ONE LAST HOPE
TO HANG ONTO.
- THIS.
- WHAT IS THAT?
A PHOTOGRAPH GIVEN TO ME
BY FUJIMOTO.
ALL THOSE YEARS I KEPT THINKING
ABOUT HOW I LONGED
TO HOLD YOU BOTH IN MY ARMS--
THE CHILDREN
YURI RISKED HER LIFE FOR.
- [ GASPS ]
- HOWEVER,
HAD THE VATICAN...
DISCOVERED THE TRUTH
OF YOUR EXISTENCE,
THEY WOULD SURELY
HAVE HUNTED YOU DOWN.
AND THAT'S THE REASON
YOU COULD NEVER COME FORWARD.
EXACTLY. BUT WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO FEAR
FROM THE GRIGORI ANYMORE.
YOU WILL BE WITH ME
FROM NOW ON.
WAIT. WHAT ABOUT MY BROTHER?
EVERYTHING YOU SAID
IS VERY IMPORTANT TO ME AND HIM.
HE SHOULD BE HERE TOO.
UNFORTUNATELY,
NOW THAT THE DEMON IN HIM
HAS AWAKENED,
I CAN'T TAKE HIM WITH US.
WHERE EXACTLY
ARE YOU TAKING ME?
[ GASPS ]
- WHAT'S THIS?
- THE DRAGOON LABORATORY,
OUR ANTIDEMON
WEAPONS UNIT.
NOW THAT THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS
HAVE BECOME MEPHISTO'S PUPPETS,
THEY CAN'T PROTECT ASSIAH
ANY LONGER.
I WANT YOU TO COME WITH ME,
YUKIO.
TOGETHER, WE CAN CREATE
A NEW ERA,
ONE THAT WILL BRING PEACE
AND FREEDOM TO ALL OF MANKIND.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
HOW DID IT GO
AT THE MONASTERY?
IT'S ALL GOOD.
THANKS TO HIS FLAMES,
ALL THE WEBS
WERE NEUTRALIZED.
THERE WERE NO CASUALTIES.
WHERE'S YUKIO?
HMM? OH, I DON'T KNOW.
HE HASN'T COME BACK HERE YET.
WHERE'D YOU TAKE
MR. NOIHAUS?
TO THE GREAT CELL.
HE'S BEING INTERROGATED.
COOL. THANKS.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
I GOT AS MUCH A RIGHT
TO LISTEN IN
AS ANYONE ELSE, DON'T I?
HEY--
YOU HEAR ABOUT NOIHAUS?
APPARENTLY,
THE VATICAN WANTS
TO GET ITS HANDS ON HIM.
REALLY? THE VATICAN?
YES. AND THE DIRECTOR'S
ALSO BEEN ARRESTED.
WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO OUR SCHOOL?
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO HELL.
LISTEN, I'VE TOLD YOU
OVER AND OVER--
SHE'S NO DEMON.
SHE'S MY WIFE.
BUT THE SPIDER WEB USED
IN THE ATTACK WAS DEFINITELY
A PRODUCT OF GEHENNA.
IF SHE'S NOT A DEMON,
THEN SHE'S POSSESSED BY ONE.
SHE'S NOT.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ RIN ]
SO YOU WERE LYING?
HMM?
YOU TOLD ME SATAN KILLED
YOUR FAMILY, REMEMBER?
SO HOW CAN A DEAD PERSON
BE WALKING AROUND,
AND WHY WOULD SHE ATTACK
MY FRIENDS?
ANSWER ME!
SHE'S AN ANTISOUL, HUH?
ANTISOUL?
[ TSUBAKI ] IT'S A TECHNIQUE
TO REVIVE A DEAD HUMAN.
REMEMBER? I BELIEVE
I TAUGHT YOU THAT IN CLASS.
OH. YEAH.
THAT THING.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
WE ALREADY KNOW
YOU RAN A LAB IN POLAND...
THAT WAS INVOLVED
IN THE RESEARCH
OF ARTIFICIAL LIFE.
SO DROP THE ACT, 'KAY?
YOU USED PROHIBITED TECHNOLOGY
TO RESURRECT YOUR DEAD WIFE.
STOP WASTING EVERYONE'S TIME
AND JUST ADMIT IT.
- IT WASN'T ME, DAMN IT.
- [ ALL GASP ]
I ADMIT I KEPT MY WIFE'S BODY
CRYOGENICALLY PRESERVED,
BUT I'D NEVER RETURN
HER SOUL TO IT.
THAT'S A LINE
THAT I WOULD NEVER CROSS.
IF I DID, I'D BE TURNED AWAY
FROM THE GATES OF HEAVEN.
IF IT WASN'T YOU,
THEN WHO WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT ONE NIGHT AT THE LAB--
[ VEHICLE APPROACHING ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
I CAME BACK TO CHECK ON HER
AS I ALWAYS DID,
BUT THIS TIME
HER CRYO TUBE WAS OPEN.
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING, FAINT ]
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
♪ [ SINGING CONTINUES, LOUDER ]
♪ [ CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
MICHELLE.
DID YOU HAVE A GOOD DAY,
MY DARLING?
[ NOIHAUS ]
RIGHT AWAY I KNEW...
HER BODY HAD BEEN POSSESSED
BY A DEMON.
BUT THE THOUGHT OF KILLING HER
WAS TOO MUCH FOR ME TO BEAR.
I COULDN'T LET HER SUFFER
THE PAIN OF DEATH AGAIN.
NO!
[ GASPING ]
MICHELLE!
IGOR NOIHAUS,
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST...
FOR RESEARCHING ARTIFICIAL LIFE
AND RESURRECTING THE DEAD.
- WHAT?
- BURN IT. BURN EVERYTHING
TO THE GROUND.
[ GASPS ]
OH.
[ SCREAMING ]
MICHELLE!
[ NOIHAUS ]
WE MANAGED TO ESCAPE.
I USED A KEY,
AND WE FLED TO JAPAN.
BUT THINGS DIDN'T GET BETTER.
I COULD TELL
SOMETHING WAS WRONG WITH HER.
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
NO!
[ GASPS ]
MICHELLE!
IT'S SO HOT!
SAVE ME!
IT'S ALL RIGHT. I'M HERE.
YOU'RE SAFE.
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ NOIHAUS ]
I THINK THAT WAS THE MOMENT
MICHELLE REMEMBERED...
BURNING TO DEATH
IN THE BLUE FLAMES.
- [ THUNDERCLAP ]
- [ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
I WON'T FORGIVE
ANYONE INVOLVED WITH SATAN.
THEY'LL ALL DIE A BLOODY DEATH.
[ THUNDERCLAP ]
[ NOIHAUS ]
MICHELLE HAD BECOME
A DEMON OF VENGEANCE.
I WANTED TO TAKE HER
BACK TO THE LAB
BEFORE SHE WAS CAUGHT,
BUT HERE I AM.
THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL US ALL THIS BEFORE?
EVEN IF I DID,
YOU BASTARDS COULDN'T SAVE HER.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH,
SHE DOESN'T HAVE
MUCH TIME LEFT ANYWAY.
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S POSSESSED
BY A DEMON, SHE'S STILL
NOTHING BUT A CORPSE.
IN A FEW DAYS SHE'LL ROT AWAY
LIKE EVERYTHING.
[ GRUNTS ]
HMM?
HOLD UP.
RIN!
[ SHURA ]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[ FOOTSTEPS RUNNING ]
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL.
I'M GOING AFTER
MR. NOIHAUS'S WIFE.
OH, YEAH?
AND THEN WHAT?
- WHAT CAN YOU DO
ABOUT ANYTHING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I CAN'T STAY HERE
AND DO NOTHING.
[ SIGHS ]
FOOLS RUSH IN
WHERE ANGELS FEAR TO TREAD.
HUH?
LOOK, I ALREADY GOT
MY FAMILIAR OUT LOOKING FOR HER.
AND TAKE THIS.
YOU'LL NEED MY TALISMAN
TO GUIDE YOU.
THANKS A LOT, SHURA.
HUH?
THAT'S "MS." SHURA.
NOW GET THE HELL OUT.
JUST REMEMBER,
AS SOON AS YOU FIND HER, CALL.
AND DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT TAKING HER ON BY YOURSELF.
RIGHT.
[ SHURA, THINKING ]
I WONDER.
WHO THE HELL WOULD RESURRECT
NOIHAUS'S WIFE?
[ RAIN FALLING ]
[ RIN, THINKING ]
HMM. I MADE IT THIS FAR,
BUT HOW DO I USE THIS THING?
MAYBE I SHOULD CALL AND ASK?
YOU'RE SUCH A USELESS FRIGGIN'
KNUCKLE-DRAGGING MORON!
SHE'D KILL ME FOR SURE.
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
UH, HELLO?
OKUMURA HERE.
- [ SHIEMI ]
RIN.
- SHIEMI?
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- I NEED YOUR HELP
WITH SOMETHING.
YES. AND HURRY.
GOTCHA.
I'M ON THE WAY.
[ GROANS ]
[ GASPING ]
[ SQUEAKING ]
WHAT'S THIS?
[ SHIEMI ]
YOU'RE AWAKE.
THANK GOODNESS.
- HUH?
- TRY NOT TO OVEREXERT
YOURSELF, OKAY?
WHERE AM I?
HOW DID I GET HERE?
- I DON'T REMEMBER.
- I FOUND YOU IN MY GARDEN.
YOU WERE UNCONSCIOUS.
I COULDN'T CARRY YOU,
BUT IT WASN'T A PROBLEM FOR HIM.
NEE!
I'M SORRY, BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU ARE.
OH, NOBODY SPECIAL.
JUST AN EXORCIST
IN TRAINING, IS ALL.
AN EXORCIST.
HELLO? ANYBODY HO--
NOPE.
NO ONE'S HOME.
AND AFTER COMING
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
NEE-EE!
OH. HEY, WHAT UP?
IS SHIEMI AROUND?
NEE! NEE, NEE!
OH, LEAD THE WAY THEN.
NEE, NEE! NEE, NEE!
NEE, NEE!
HEY, SHIEMI!
WHAT THE--
NEE, NEE-EE.
I DON'T REMEMBER SEEING
THESE STEPS BEFORE.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SHURA'S FAMILIAR?
NO WAY.
THAT MEANS SHE'S HERE.
THIS WAS MY GRANDMA'S
SECRET GARDEN.
SHE LEFT IT TO ME
TO TAKE CARE OF.
- OH.
- MY GRANDMA USED
TO ALWAYS TELL ME...
THAT IF I JUST STOPPED
AND LISTENED TO WHAT THE PLANTS
WERE SAYING,
THEY'D BE SURE TO BLOSSOM.
AND YOU KNOW?
SHE WAS RIGHT.
LOOK AROUND.
THERE'S NO DOUBT
GRANDMA COULD HEAR THEIR VOICES.
IT'S AMAZING TO THINK
HOW MUCH ALL THE FAIRIES
IN THE GARDEN LOVED HER.
BUT THEN MY GRANDMA
WAS AN AMAZING PERSON.
OH! I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO GO ON AND ON LIKE THAT.
I GUESS THIS IS WHAT
THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA
WOULD BE LIKE.
HUH?
MY HUSBAND TOLD ME
ABOUT IT ONCE.
HE SAID IT'S A PLACE
GOD MADE...
WHERE ALL THE PLANTS
IN THE WORLD
HAD BEEN GATHERED.
IF THERE REALLY IS
A GARDEN LIKE THAT,
I'M SURE IT WOULD BE
A LOT LIKE HERE.
UM, IF YOU WANT,
COULD WE BE FRIENDS?
BESIDES GRANDMA,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I'VE MET...
WHO KNOWS ABOUT
THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA.
MM. YOUR HANDS ARE SO WARM.
UM, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
MY NAME?
MY NAME IS
SHIEMI MORIYAMA.
- I'M MICHELLE.
- SHIEMI.
- [ GASPS ]
- RIN?
GET AWAY FROM HER RIGHT NOW!
[ GASPING ]
STAY BACK!
- LET HER GO!
- SO YOU'RE WITH SATAN TOO.
I SHOULD'VE GUESSED.
HUH?
SHIEMI'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
I WILL HAVE MY REVENGE.
EVERYTHING I EVER LOVED
WAS BURNED TO ASHES.
BLUE FLAMES
BURNED IT ALL AWAY!
I WON'T FORGIVE SATAN FOR THAT.
HE TOOK EVERYTHING I LOVED
AWAY FROM ME,
AND TO MAKE HIM PAY,
I'M GOING TO--
I'LL TAKE... EVERYTHING
AWAY FROM YOU.
I SWEAR.
[ GASPS ]
- SHIEMI!
- MICHELLE?
[ GRUNTS ]
NO, WAIT!
SHE'S HURT REALLY BAD.
I'VE GOT TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
YOU CAN'T HELP HER.
SHE'S ALREADY DEAD.
WHAT?
SHE'S A CORPSE
THAT WAS BROUGHT BACK TO LIFE
TO GET REVENGE ON SATAN.
SO GET BACK, SHIEMI.
YOU CAN'T.
MICHELLE'S NOT EVIL.
I KNOW IT.
SHE TRIED TO KILL SUGURO,
THE GUYS AND EVERYONE
AT THE MONASTERY.
NONE OF MY FRIENDS ARE SAFE
AS LONG AS SHE'S AROUND.
I DIDN'T CALL YOU
BECAUSE I WAS IN DANGER.
I CALLED YOU BECAUSE
I NEEDED YOUR HELP.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M HERE--
TO HELP YOU.
I'LL PROTECT YOU
FROM THAT THING.
NO!
I NEVER ASKED YOU TO DO THAT!
SHIEMI.
LOOK AT HER.
IF SHE'S EVIL,
NEE AND THE OTHERS...
WOULDN'T HAVE TAKEN TO HER
LIKE THAT.
[ FAIRIES ]
NEE!
YOU SEE?
[ SIGHS ]
BY THE WAY, SHE'S
MR. NOIHAUS'S WIFE.
WHAT?
[ BUSY TONE ]
[ RIN ]
CAN'T GET A SIGNAL HERE.
I GOTTA MAKE A CALL.
I'LL BE BACK IN A SEC.
OKAY.
[ RIN ] HELLO?
[ SHURA ]
HEY, RIN. WHAT'S UP?
I FOUND HER.
YOU DID? SERIOUSLY?
WHERE IS SHE?
THE SUPPLY SHOP.
WHAT THE HELL
IS SHE DOING THERE?
HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
I JUST GOT HERE.
I'M COMING OVER
AND BRINGING NOIHAUS.
DON'T LET HER OUT
OF YOUR SIGHT.
YOU GOT THAT?
ACTUALLY, DON'T COME OVER.
FOR REAL. DON'T.
HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, RIN?
SOMETHING GOING ON?
HEY--
[ BEEPS ]
[ ANGEL ]
WHAT A MAGNIFICENT GARDEN.
IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
DEFINITELY NOT A PLACE
FOR DEMONS.
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GUNS COCKING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ MAN ]
SIR AUGUSTE,
WE'VE CAPTURED THE SUSPECT.
RIN!
SO YOU WERE HIDING HERE
THE WHOLE TIME,
YOU DEMON IN HUMAN SKIN.
[ GRUNTING ]
THERE IS NO GREATER TABOO
THAN RESURRECTING THE DEAD.
IT VIOLATES
THE LAWS OF ASSIAH.
I CONDEMN YOU
IN THE NAME OF THE VATICAN.
- MICHELLE!
- [ MUFFLED ]
STOP!
HMM.
[ SWORD RINGING ]
OUT OF MY WAY!
[ NOIHAUS ]
I WILL ATONE FOR ALL
OF MICHELLE'S CRIMES.
PLEASE HAVE MERCY ON HER.
LET MY WIFE GO.
I BEG YOU.
BRAVO TO YOU AND YOUR
MATRIMONIAL COMMITMENTS.
- [ GRUNTS ]
- SPARE ME!
THE DEAD SHALL ONLY BE
RESURRECTED AT THE RAPTURE...
WHEN THE ANGELS
BLOW THEIR TRUMPETS
FOR THE LAST TIME!
STOP IT!
[ GROANS, GASPS ]
DEFENDING DEMONS NOW,
SON OF SATAN?
NO. I JUST THINK YOU GUYS SUCK
FOR BUSTING IN HERE
AND TEARING THE PLACE UP.
I'M WARNING YOU, DEMON.
BY DEFYING ME, YOU'RE ALSO
DEFYING THE VATICAN.
LIKE I GIVE A RAT'S ASS
WHAT YOU SAY.
- RIN!
- [ STEEL CLANGING ]
[ THINKING ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THE SON OF SATAN
FIGHTING TO PROTECT US.
AND AFTER I TRIED TO TAKE
EVERYTHING AWAY
THAT WAS DEAR TO HIM. WHY?
IS THAT THE BEST YOU CAN DO,
SATAN'S SPAWN?
YOU WANNA GO?
LET'S GO!
[ SHOUTING ]
SNAKE FANG!
[ SHOUTING, GRUNTS ]
WHAT THE HELL?
SHURA?
WOULD YOU JUST CHILL?
YOU ARE NOT HELPING ANYONE.
JUST GET OUT OF MY WAY.
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
REALLY?
COME ON, THINK.
OUT OF MY WAY!
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ SCREAMS ]
- MICHELLE!
- OH, NO.
[ NOIHAUS GASPING ]
STAY WITH ME, MICHELLE.
MICHELLE!
DAMN IT!
WHICH ONE OF YOU SHOT HER, HUH?
WHICH ONE OF YOU COWARDS WAS IT?
- STOP IT, RIN!
- COME ON!
I'LL TAKE ALL OF YOU--
- THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA.
- STEP UP, YOU DA--
THAT PARADISE
WHERE ALL THE PLANTS
IN THE WORLD ARE GATHERED.
IT'S NOT HERE,
BUT I KNOW IT'S REAL.
IF WE CAN JUST FIND IT,
I KNOW WE CAN LIVE IN PEACE.
WE CAN FIND IT TOGETHER,
JUST YOU AND ME.
MY DARLING.
[ ANGEL ]
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
ARREST THOSE HERETICS!
THAT'S AN ORDER!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
[ SHOUTING ]
- [ GASPS ]
- [ ALL ]
NEE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SO MANY
BABY GREENMEN BEFORE.
CURSES!
[ BELLS TOLLING ]
[ MAN ]
SIR AUGUSTE.
YES, I KNOW.
RETREAT.
WHAT'S UP WITH
ALL THE BELLS?
IT'S AN EMERGENCY SUMMONS
FROM THE VATICAN.
THAT CAN'T BE A GOOD THING.
HEY, YOU THINK IT'S GONNA
WORK OUT FOR THEM?
I HOPE IT DOES.
IF ANYONE CAN FIND IT, THEY CAN.
THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA,
A PLACE WHERE THEY CAN
LIVE IN PEACE.
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
ARTHUR AUGUSTE ANGEL
AT YOUR SERVICE, MILORD.
[ MAN ]
THANK YOU FOR YOUR DILIGENCE,
PALADIN.
WHERE ARE THE GRIGORI?
I'VE RELIEVED THEM.
IMPOSSIBLE!
THEY ARE THE SUPREME ADVISERS TO
THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS.
THAT'S ALL IN THE PAST NOW.
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
I, ERNST FREDERIK EGIN,
WILL TAKE COMMAND OF
THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ EGIN ]
GENTLEMEN, THROUGHOUT HISTORY,
HUMANITY HAS BEEN
ON THE DEFENSIVE.
TODAY WE TAKE THE FIGHT
TO THEM.
WE SHALL DESTROY THE DEMONS
AND BRING PEACE TO OUR WORLD
FOREVERMORE!
YUKIO OKUMURA.
[ SHIEMI ]
HEY, RIN, IS THIS REALLY
WHAT AN EXORCIST'S JOB IS?
I DON'T FEEL RIGHT ABOUT THIS.
[ RIN ]
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
[ YUKIO ]
YOU'D BETTER LET GO OF ME, RIN.
I SAID LET GO OF ME!