[ RIN SCREAMING ]
I OVERSLEPT!
[ PANTING ]
THANK YOU FOR THE MEAL.
GOOD MORNING, RIN.
COME ON, MAN!
WHY DIDN'T YOU WAKE ME UP?
I TRIED THREE SEPARATE TIMES,
BUT YOU WOULDN'T MOVE.
I FIGURED YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
PRETTY WIPED OUT,
SO I JUST LET YOU SLEEP IN.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU'RE PLAYING
THE GOOD BROTHER, TOMORROW
TRY FOUR TIMES.
THANKS FOR BREAKFAST.
[ GULPING ]
SHOULDN'T YOU GO?
I GOTTA FUEL UP.
I'M RUNNING A MARATHON
THIRD PERIOD.
[ GULPING ]
WELL, I'M GONNA START
HEADING OUT.
DON'T EAT SO FAST, RIN.
AT THE PACE YOU'RE EATING,
YOU'RE GOING TO POP.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU,
MY MOM?
[ GULPING ]
AH! THANKS FOR THE MEAL.
♪ [ MAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ BELLS CHIMING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ CLAMORING ]
[ GROWLS ]
DAMN, I'M LATE.
I GOTCHA!
[ GASPS ]
SUGURO!
WE GOT A NEW FACE
IN THE LUNCH LINE TODAY.
HEY, THERE, OKUMURA.
HOW'S IT GOING?
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- YOU WANNA LET THAT BUN GO?
COME ON, HANDS OFF.
THAT YAKISOBA BUN'S MINE, MAN!
I GRABBED IT FIRST,
SO BACK YOUR ASS OFF!
CALM DOWN, BON.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S A LITTLE CHILDISH?
LOOK HERE, KONEKOMARU,
A GRUDGE OVER FOOD
CAN LAST SEVEN GENERATIONS.
WE GOTTA NIP THIS IN THE BUD
RIGHT NOW BEFORE IT CAUSES
ALL KINDS OF PROBLEMS.
WHOA, YOUR NAME'S KONEKOMARU?
THAT'S A PRETTY COOL NAME.
HEY, I'M TALKING TO YOU!
I'M TOO LATE.
[ GIRLS ]
HI, YUKIO.
UH, DO I KNOW YOU?
NO, BUT WE'RE FRESHMEN
IN THE SAME ADVANCED CLASS
AS YOU. I'M KASHINO.
I'M NISHIWAKI.
I'M OMOTO.
OH, UH, CAN I HELP YOU?
WELL, IN CASE YOU MISSED
HAVING LUNCH TODAY--
WE DIDN'T WANT YOU TO GO HUNGRY,
SO WE MADE LUNCH JUST FOR YOU.
THE ONE I MADE
IS THE BEST.
[ ALL GROWLING ]
HEY, MY LUNCH
IS FIRST.
YEAH, RIGHT. MINE IS.
UM--
WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
I GUESS
OUR YOUNG TEACHER'S
PRETTY POPULAR.
[ MIWA ]
THE POLAR OPPOSITE
OF HIS BROTHER.
MAN, KONEKOMARU,
YOU'RE A FUNNY GUY.
HEY, WHEN DID YOU
BECOME BUDDIES?
[ ARGUING ]
THERE'S RIN.
UM, ACTUALLY, I JUST REMEMBERED
I'M SUPPOSED TO HAVE LUNCH...
WITH MY BROTHER TODAY,
SO EXCUSE ME, LADIES, GOTTA GO.
- [ ALL SHOUT ]
- COME WITH ME!
WHAT'S WITH THEM?
WEIRDOS.
[ PANTING ]
YOU SAVED ME...
BACK THERE.
THANK YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU BAILED
ON THOSE GIRLS AFTER THEY
MADE YOU ALL THAT FOOD.
WHY DIDN'T YOU EAT THE LUNCHES,
MAN? WHAT A WASTE.
THINK ABOUT IT-- I CAN'T EAT
THREE LUNCHES AT ONCE.
AND IF I ONLY PICKED
ONE OF THEM, THE OTHER GIRLS
WOULD GET UPSET.
WHOA! CHECK OUT THIS SPREAD!
THIS CAFETERIA'S GOT LOBSTER
ON THE MENU.
- DID YOU HEAR
ANYTHING I SAID?
- [ RIN ] WOW!
FRENCH, CHINESE, ITALIAN--
THEY'VE GOT EVERYTHING.
[ YUKIO ]
OF COURSE. TRUE CROSS ACADEMY'S
A SCHOOL FOR THE PRIVILEGED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I FINALLY MADE IT
INTO THE WORLD OF HIGH SOCIETY.
YOU HAVE TO BUY A TICKET
FROM THE VENDING MACHINE FIRST.
♪ WONDER WHAT I'LL GET ♪
WHAT THE HELL?
TELL ME THESE PRICES HAVE
AN EXTRA ZERO ON THE END.
AGAIN, THIS IS
A RICH KIDS' SCHOOL.
STUCK UP RICH KIDS,
WHEN I GET THROUGH WITH YOU--
[ GROWLS ]
CALM DOWN, RIN.
THE "A" LUNCH
IS ONLY 1,800 YEN.
I'LL PAY FOR IT
IF YOU JUST CALM DOWN.
[ MEPHISTO ]
YOU WANT ME TO LOWER THE PRICES?
I'M AFRAID
THAT WON'T BE POSSIBLE.
TO PROVIDE FIRST-RATE CUISINE,
WE MUST PURCHASE
FIRST-RATE INGREDIENTS,
HIRE FIRST-RATE CHEFS,
ETCETERA, ETCETERA.
WHY FIRST RATE?
IT'S A STUDENT
CAFETERIA.
DINING IS CULTURE.
A PERSON'S LIFE IS ENRICHED...
BY EXPERIENCING
FIRST-RATE CUISINE.
[ CHIMING ]
FINALLY.
[ SLURPING ]
THIS COMING
FROM SOMEONE EATING
INSTANT NOODLES?
AT LEAST GIVE US AN ALLOWANCE
SO WE CAN EAT, MAN.
UH-OH. HOW COULD I FORGET
SUCH AN IMPORTANT DETAIL.
SO SORRY.
YOU ARE THE SON OF SATAN,
BUT EVEN YOU NEED A LITTLE CASH
TO GET YOU THROUGH THE DAY.
A 2,000 YEN BILL!
THOSE THINGS ARE
SUPPOSED TO BE SUPER RARE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE ACTUALLY HAS ONE.
I CAN BUY 10 YAKISOBA BUNS
WITH THIS.
OH, BEFORE I FORGET,
YOU'LL BE PAID
ON THE 10TH OF EVERY MONTH.
HUH?
FOR THE WHOLE MONTH?
THIS? FOR BOTH OF US?
CORRECT.
ARE YOU OUT
OF YOUR MIND?
DO I DETECT DISPLEASURE?
YOU CAN HAVE THIS
HUNDRED YEN NOTE INSTEAD.
IT'S OBSOLETE, BUT THE PORTRAIT
IS MY PERSONAL FAVORITE.
LIKE I CARE WHAT YOUR
FREAKING FAVORITES ARE.
[ GROWLS ]
CONTROL YOURSELF,
RIN!
[ YUKIO ]
REMEMBER WHAT DAD
USED TO SAY?
"MAN SHALL NOT LIVE
BY BREAD ALONE."
DAD'S LECTURES AREN'T GONNA FILL
OUR STOMACHS, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, ARE YOU COOL WITH THIS?
ARE YOU SATISFIED WITH THE LAME
ALLOWANCE OF 2,000 YEN A MONTH?
WELL, I HAVE MY JOB
AS AN INSTRUCTOR,
AND I GET PAID PRETTY WELL
AS AN EXORCIST, SO I'M GOOD.
YOU TRAITOR! I'M GONNA--
[ GRUNTS ]
HOLD IT.
I KNOW HOW YOU CAN MAKE IT
THOUGH SCHOOL...
WITHOUT STARVING
TO DEATH.
HUH?
- DO OUR OWN COOKING?
- YEAH. I'LL GIVE YOU
THE MONEY TO BUY GROCERIES,
AND THEN YOU CAN MAKE LUNCH
FOR THE TWO OF US.
THAT WAY I CAN SAVE
A LITTLE BIT OF MONEY,
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT STARVING.
BESIDES, COOKING'S
THE ONLY THING YOU DO WELL.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT EVERYONE SAYS--
GIRLS LIKE GUYS WHO CAN COOK.
FOR REAL?
THIS IS MY OPPORTUNITY
TO BE AWESOME.
HE'LL HAVE TO GET UP EARLY
IF HE HAS TO MAKE LUNCH.
AND IF THOSE GIRLS
OFFER ME LUNCH AGAIN,
I'LL HAVE AN EXCUSE.
I'LL JUST SAY, "GEE, THANKS,
BUT I BROUGHT MY OWN. SORRY."
I GET TO KILL TWO-- NO, FOUR--
BIRDS WITH ONE LUNCH.
UH, WHERE AM I GONNA COOK?
IT'LL BE HARD
WITHOUT A KITCHEN IN OUR ROOM.
YOU CAN USE
THE MAIN KITCHEN.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
LIVING THERE.
WE'VE GOT THE WHOLE BUILDING
ALL TO OURSELVES.
[ CHOPPING VEGETABLES ]
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO COOK THIS LATE AT NIGHT.
CAN'T YOU DO IT
TOMORROW MORNING?
YOU ALWAYS MAKE YOUR LUNCH
THE NIGHT BEFORE
AND STICK IT IN THE FREEZER.
THE NEXT DAY YOU TAKE
YOUR FROZEN LUNCH TO SCHOOL
AND LET IT THAW DURING CLASS.
IT SHOULD BE READY TO EAT
BY NOON.
YOU COULD SAY
IT'S SORT OF A HOUSEWIFE'S TIP.
OH, REALLY?
IT WOULD BE PRETTY AMAZING...
IF YOU COULD SPEND THAT AMOUNT
OF ENERGY ON YOUR STUDIES.
WHO ASKED YOU?
TAKE A CRAP AND GO TO BED.
YES, SIR.
GOOD NIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
I'M ALL DONE.
- [ CLATTERING ]
- [ GASPS ]
WAS THAT A MOUSE?
HUH? OH, GEEZ,
IT'S REALLY LATE.
[ FOOTSTEPS RECEDE ]
[ FOOTSTEPS RUNNING ]
- HMM?
- YOU FOUR-EYED
MOLE FACE!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHO ARE YOU CALLING
A FOUR-EYED MOLE FACE?
SHUT UP!
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
HOW HUNGRY YOU WERE!
IN THIS HOUSE,
THERE'S THINGS YOU NEVER DO!
- HUH?
- DON'T PLAY DUMB!
THAT FOOD I COOKED WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE FOR OUR LUNCH!
BUT YOU ATE IT ALL, DIDN'T YOU?
COME ON, YOU KNOW I'D NEVER
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
OKAY, WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHO DID?
YOU SAID WE'RE
THE ONLY ONES LIVING
IN THIS BUILDING, REMEMBER?
WE ARE ALONE, AREN'T WE?
WE'RE NOT.
WHENEVER IT WAS TIME TO EAT,
THE FOOD WAS ALWAYS READY,
WAITING FOR US
DOWN IN THE KITCHEN.
[ RIN ]
WE DIDN'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
WHO WAS DOING THE COOKING.
SO THEN WHO COOKED
ALL THOSE MEALS?
[ CHOPPING ECHOES ]
- THEY'RE HERE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT WHO?
[ CHOPPING CONTINUES ]
GENTLEMEN, MORNING.
MEPHISTO?
ALL THIS TIME IT WAS YOU?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S BEEN
COOKING ALL OUR MEALS FOR US
SINCE WE MOVED IN?
I'VE BEEN DOING
NO SUCH THING.
I'M JUST A TEMPORARY
REPLACEMENT.
[ BOTH ]
A REPLACEMENT?
TEMPORARY. THE ONE WHO'S
IN CHARGE OF YOUR MEALS
IS UKOBACH.
UKOBACH?
I KNOW THAT NAME.
I THINK HE'S A STOVE SPIRIT.
HE SNEAKS INTO THE KITCHEN
WHEN HUMANS ARE SLEEPING,
AND HE MAKES THE FOOD
TASTE BETTER.
SPOKEN LIKE A TRUE INSTRUCTOR.
GOOD ANSWER.
UP TO NOW, HE'S BEEN LOYALLY
CARRYING OUT HIS DUTIES HERE
AS MY FAMILIAR.
YESTERDAY, THOUGH,
THE TWO OF YOU HAD APPARENTLY
TRESPASSED ON HIS TERRITORY--
THE KITCHEN.
NOW HE'S IN A FOUL MOOD,
AND HAS BOYCOTTED HIS JOB.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND
THE GRAVITY
OF THE SITUATION.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT IS THIS?
MY SPECIALTY--
"LITTLE DEMON-FLAVORED" OATMEAL.
PLEASE, HELP YOURSELVES.
[ GAGGING ]
GO ON.
DON'T BE SHY.
HERE GOES!
[ SCREAMING ]
RIN, NO!
ARE YOU OKAY?
I HEAR GRANDMA CALLING ME.
GRANDMA?
WE NEVER MET OUR GRANDMA.
WHOEVER SHE IS,
DON'T FOLLOW HER
INTO THE LIGHT.
A FAMILIAR'S MISCONDUCT
IS THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF ITS MASTER.
UNTIL UKOBACH'S MOOD IMPROVES,
I WILL TAKE CHARGE
OF THIS KITCHEN AND PREPARE
ALL YOUR MEALS PERSONALLY.
WHAT IF HIS MOOD
DOESN'T IMPROVE?
HMM, I WILL BECOME
YOUR PERSONAL COOK...
FOR THE DURATION
OF YOUR TIME HERE.
- RIN!
- SO, THIS UKOBACH GUY
OR WHATEVER,
I'M SO GONNA KICK HIS ASS.
IDIOT. YOU WILL NOT
KICK THE CHEF.
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ THUNDERCLAP ]
OKAY. I PUT EVERYTHING BACK
THE WAY IT WAS.
SO HOW ABOUT
YOU GET OVER IT ALREADY?
[ GASPS ]
OH, COME ON.
YOU'RE STILL MAD?
WHAT ARE YOU SO PISSED OFF
ABOUT ANYWAY?
IF YOU DON'T WANNA COOK ANYMORE,
THEN GET OUT.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE AROUND
HERE WHO CAN COOK, YOU KNOW.
[ THUNDERCLAP ]
SO THAT'S WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE.
[ PANTING ]
I THOUGHT
I COULD LEAVE RIN ALONE
BECAUSE SIR PHELES WAS THERE.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
[ THUNDERCLAP ]
RIN!
[ PANTING ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ PANTING ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
- RIN!
- [ APPLAUSE ]
SIR PHELES, WHAT HAPPENED?
THEY FOUGHT BRAVELY TO WITHIN
AN INCH OF THEIR LIVES.
THEIR POWERS WERE LET LOOSE,
EXPLODING THROUGH THE KITCHEN.
[ SHOUTING ]
[ YUKIO ]
THEY HAD A COOKING BATTLE?
BY FLEXING THEIR CULINARY
MUSCLES, THEY DISCOVERED
EACH OTHER'S TALENTS.
BEHOLD--
A NEW FRIENDSHIP IS BORN.
YOUR FRIED RICE
WAS SO AWESOME, MAN.
[ SQUEAKING ]
HUH? DID YOU JUST CALL
MY KATSU BOWL EXCEPTIONAL?
LET'S DO IT!
WE'RE GONNA MAKE
THE ULTIMATE LUNCH.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
ARE YOU IN?
[ SQUEAKS ]
THAT'S MY BROTHER.
DEFYING LOGIC
ALL KINDS OF WAYS.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
A HOMEMADE LUNCH?
UH, YES.
LOOKS YUMMY.
OH, WOW. NOT ONLY ARE YOU
A TOP STUDENT, BUT YOU'RE ALSO
A SUPER AMAZING COOK.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
MY BROTHER MADE THIS.
[ TOGETHER ]
YOUR BROTHER?
YES. MY BROTHER'S
A REALLY TALENTED COOK.
RIGHT ON, YUKIO.
KEEP PLUGGING MY SKILLS
IN THE KITCHEN.
WOW! IT'S YUKIO'S
BIG BROTHER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU MADE
THAT AWESOME LUNCH BY YOURSELF.
YOU'RE COOL.
AND SO BEGINS
THE FIRST STUD PHASE
OF MY LIFE.
[ OMOTO ]
IS THAT YOUR BROTHER?
[ KASHINO ]
HOW WOULD A CREEP LIKE THAT
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT COOKING?
[ SHOUTS ]
I WANT YOU
TO TEACH ME TO COOK.
[ NISHIWAKI ]
AND ME!
TEACH ME TOO!
WHAT THE HELL?
THERE'S OKUMURA.
LOOKS LIKE HE'S CRYING
OVER HIS LUNCH.
THAT POOR GUY.
HE MUST REALLY BE HUNGRY.
BETTER NOT LOOK HIM IN THE EYE.
STUPIDITY'S CONTAGIOUS.
[ RIN ]
GIRLS LIKE GUYS
WHO CAN COOK. YEAH, RIGHT.
ALL I DID WAS MAKE YUKIO LOOK
GOOD AND ME LOOK LIKE A JERK.
SHIEMI?
[ SQUEALS ]
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT YOU DOING HERE?
- UH--
- SHIEMI?
OH, HI.
WHAT BRINGS YOU
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE?
WE JUST GOT OUR SHIPMENT
OF MALACHITE,
SO I BROUGHT YOUR ORDER.
THANK YOU FOR DOING THAT.
UM, WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME IN
AND HAVE SOME TEA?
SURE. ALTHOUGH--
IT'S COOL.
DON'T BE SHY.
COME ON IN.
OH.
SEE THAT?
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT GIRL?
THE NERVE.
WALTZING INTO YUKIO'S DORM
LIKE IT'S NO BIG THING.
IS SHE HIS GIRLFRIEND?
[ BOTH GASP ]
OF COURSE NOT.
HE'S GOT BETTER TASTE
THAN THAT.
YEAH. SHE'S PROBABLY
THE HOUSEKEEPER.
IF SHE'S THE HOUSEKEEPER,
WHY WOULD HE INVITE HER IN
FOR TEA?
[ GRUMBLING ]
YEAH, WELL, WHATEVER.
WE CAN'T JUST TURN AROUND
AND GO HOME.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
WITH ALL THE LUNCHES WE MADE?
I SAY WE WAIT RIGHT HERE
UNTIL THAT COW LEAVES.
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ SHIEMI ]
HE'S A FAMILIAR?
HE'S THE HEAD CHEF
OF OUR DORM.
UKOBACH EVEN MADE
THE TEA WE'RE HAVING.
TRY IT.
DELICIOUS.
IT'S YUMMY, MR. UKOBACH.
- [ SQUEAKING ]
- OH, NO.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
I REALLY SHOULD
GET GOING NOW.
NOT TO WORRY.
I CAN HELP.
I HAVE THIS KEY WHICH LINKS
THE DORM TO THE SUPPLY SHOP,
REMEMBER?
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I FORGOT.
I ACTUALLY WALKED
ALL THE WAY OVER HERE.
I'LL SEE YOU HOME.
THANKS, YUKI.
[ FAKING LAUGHTER ]
SHE SAID, "THANKS, YUKI."
KILL ME.
[ GROWLS ]
HOW LONG YOU GONNA KEEP WAVING?
- [ SQUEAKING ]
- OH, YOU THINK
IT'S GOOD ENOUGH...
IF SHE ENJOYED YOUR FOOD
AND SAID IT WAS DELICIOUS.
YEAH, WELL, NO ONE ASKED
FOR YOUR OPINION.
[ DOG BARKING, DISTANT ]
SO, UH, HOW LONG
ARE WE GONNA WAIT OUT HERE?
IT'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT.
LET'S GO.
YOU CAN GO IF YOU WANT TO.
THAT GIRL HASN'T LEFT,
AND NEITHER WILL I.
HEY, GUYS, YOU DON'T THINK
SHE'S GONNA SPEND THE NIGHT
WITH, LIKE, YUKIO, DO YOU?
[ BOTH ]
WHAT?
THAT DOES IT.
WE'RE GONNA BREAK IN THERE.
[ KASHINO ]
WHICH ROOM IS YUKIO'S?
[ NISHIWAKI ]
IT'S ROOM 602.
[ OMOTO ]
WAIT. CAN'T YOU SMELL THAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SMELLS LIKE SOMEONE'S
BEEN COOKING.
[ SHRIEKS ]
IS THAT WHAT HE'S HAVING
FOR LUNCH TOMORROW?
HUH. WONDER IF SHE MADE IT.
[ BOTH GASP ]
I MADE OCTOPUS-SHAPED
SAUSAGES.
AND FRIED CALAMARI TOO.
NO!
I'LL SHOW HER!
THAT BITCH!
[ SHOUTING ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
HE WON'T EVEN LAY A CHOPSTICK
ON ALL THE YUMMY LUNCHES
THAT WE MAKE FOR HIM.
BUT HE GOES AND EATS
WHATEVER CRAP
THAT GIRL MAKES FOR HIM.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
IT'S UNFORGIVABLE.
[ GROWLING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ GIRLS SCREAMING ]
HOLY CRAP!
WHO'S SCREAMING?
UKOBACH?
YOU ARE UKOBACH, RIGHT?
[ ROARS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON, UKOBACH?
HOLY SHIT.
THOSE ARE MY CLASSMATES.
I THINK I KNOW
WHAT CAUSED THIS,
BUT I'M HAVING A HARD TIME
PROCESSING IT.
[ GROWLS ]
HE STARTED COOKING.
THIS AIN'T RIGHT.
YEAH, THANKS.
I CAN SEE THAT.
IF HE'S MAKING A STEW,
HE'S GOTTA THROW IN
SOME GINGER AND BAY LEAVES...
TO GET RID
OF THAT MEATY SMELL.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
IT'S A BASIC RULE
OF COOKING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S FORGOTTEN ALL ABOUT IT.
OKAY, GUY, HOLD UP.
DO YOU WANNA TELL ME WHAT
THE HELL YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
[ GRUNTS ]
RIN!
UKOBACH, REMEMBER
WHAT YOU SAID.
A LITTLE WHILE AGO YOU SAID IF
SOMEONE'S ENJOYED YOUR COOKING,
AND TOLD YOU IT WAS DELICIOUS,
THAT WAS GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
[ MAN ]
WHAT'S UP WITH THIS OMELET?
SALTY.
WATCH OUT. I FOUND
AN EGGSHELL IN IT.
WHO MADE THIS STUFF?
RIN? NO WAY.
YOU MADE THIS?
IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
THEN YOU DON'T HAVE TO EAT IT.
HEY.
HUH?
DON'T YOU GO WASTING FOOD
LIKE THAT.
HEY, GIVE THAT BACK.
OH, SO YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO MADE THE OMELET, HUH?
- [ GULPING ]
- [ GASPS ]
NOT BAD
FOR YOUR FIRST TIME.
THANK YOU FOR THE MEAL, RIN.
[ RIN ]
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT.
COOKING'S ALL ABOUT
SEEING PEOPLE HAPPY...
ABOUT SOMETHING
YOU MADE FOR THEM.
IF SOMEONE LIKES MY FOOD,
IT MAKES ME HAPPY.
THAT'S WHY I LOVE TO COOK.
AND EVERY TIME I DO IT,
I WANNA MAKE SOMETHING
EVEN BETTER.
TAKE A LOOK
AT WHAT YOU'RE COOKING NOW.
YOU THINK ANYONE'S
GONNA EAT THAT
AND SAY IT'S DELICIOUS?
[ ROARING ]
[ HIGH VOICE ]
WHY?
WHY WON'T YOU EAT IT?
UKOBACH SAID SOMETHING.
HANG ON. HEAR THAT?
IT'S NOT HIM.
WE WORKED HARD MAKING
THOSE LUNCHES FOR YOU.
WE WANTED YOU TO EAT THEM.
THAT'S ALL, YUKIO.
I GET IT.
THEY FELT SLIGHTED.
AND THAT MADE UKOBACH
LOSE CONTROL.
THAT MEANS...
IT'S YOUR FAULT,
YOU JACKASS!
UH-OH.
HERE YOU GO.
THOSE GIRLS POURED THEIR HEARTS
INTO MAKING THESE, SO DIG IN.
GO ON. IT'S NICE AND SALTY,
JUST THE WAY YOU LIKE IT.
[ GROANING ]
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING TO ME?
[ SHOUTING ]
[ MEPHISTO ]
AND THEN YOU ATE...
EVERY LAST BITE OF FOOD
IN THAT LUNCH BOX
ALL BY YOURSELF?
BRILLIANT SOLUTION,
INSTRUCTOR OKUMURA.
I COMMEND YOU.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY YOURSELF
ABOUT THOSE STUDENTS.
AS OF TODAY,
THEY'VE RETURNED TO CLASS.
AND THANKS TO YOUR SACRIFICE,
UKOBACH HAS RETURNED
TO HIS SENSES.
AS A REWARD,
TAKE THE NEXT TWO DAYS OFF
AND HAVE A NICE REST.
TOODLES.
[ BEEPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
WHAT UP?
WHAT IS THAT?
WE WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
TO, YOU KNOW, HELP PERK YOU UP,
SO WE MADE YOU THIS LITTLE DISH
WE LIKE TO CALL
"THE STAMINA LUNCH."
[ GROANING, GAGS ]
GO AHEAD, DIG IN.
STUFF THAT FACE.
[ SQUEAKS ]
I HATE LUNCH.
♪ [ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ YUKIO ]
STARTING MONDAY,
WE'RE OFFERING
A WEEKLONG BOOT CAMP
TO PREPARE YOU FOR THE EXAM.
[ RIN ]
SHIEMI? EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT YOU DOING DOWN THERE?
[ SHIEMI ]
I, UH--
I'D LIKE TO--
WOULD YOU PLEASE BE MY FRIEND?