HEY, RIN.
COME ON, WAKE UP.
[ MUMBLES ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ SCREECHES ]
OW!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ KURO ]
YUKIO DIDN'T COME HOME
LAST NIGHT, HUH?
THAT DAMN YUKIO.
IF HE WAS GONNA STAY OUT
ALL NIGHT,
LEAST HE COULD'VE DONE IS CALL.
CRAP! I'M GONNA BE LATE!
♪ [ MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ CHATTERING ]
WHAT'S WITH ALL
THE COMMOTION?
OH, HEY, OKUMURA.
HEY, MAN,
HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY, SO WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON?
THAT HOSTAGE CRISIS
A COUPLE DAYS AGO, THAT'S WHAT.
AND THERE'S A RUMOR GOING AROUND
THE DIRECTOR TOOK THE BLAME
FOR IT AND WAS FORCED TO RESIGN.
HUH?
THEY'RE SHUTTING THE ACADEMY
DOWN FOR THE TIME BEING.
THEY WON'T EVEN LET US
GET INTO THE BUILDING TO GET
OUR BOOKS AND STUFF OUT.
- THAT'S ONLY HALF OF IT.
- [ SHIMA ]
GOOD MORNING, IZUMO.
THE VATICAN'S HIGHER-UPS
HAVE ALL BEEN KICKED OUT.
THE POPE'S BEEN REMOVED,
AND A NEW ONE'S BEEN NAMED.
THEY COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
A WORSE TIME.
DO YOU THINK ALL THIS
HAS ANYTHING TO DO WITH
THE DIRECTOR GETTING CANNED?
I DON'T KNOW.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE,
SOMEONE'S MAKING
BIG CHANGES AROUND HERE--
FOR THE CRAM SCHOOL
AND FOR THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
[ MAN ]
ALL OF THE INSTRUCTORS
AT THE CRAM SCHOOL,
ALONG WITH THE JAPAN
BRANCH OF THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS,
WILL BE MAKING
A FRESH START
OF THINGS...
UNDER THE DIRECT SUPERVISION
OF VATICAN HEADQUARTERS.
TODAY THE JAPAN BRANCH
OF THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS
HAS A NEW DIRECTOR.
HE'S BEEN APPOINTED
BY THE VATICAN,
SO GIVE HIM YOUR ATTENTION.
[ MURMURING ]
[ YUKIO ]
SINCE YOU ALL KNOW ME,
WE CAN SKIP THE FORMALITIES
AND GET TO THE HEART
OF THE MATTER.
- I AM YOUR NEW DIRECTOR.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
OKUMURA?
I KNOW,
AND HE'S STILL A STUDENT.
WHY, BY RANK HE'S JUST
INTERMEDIATE FIRST CLASS
LIKE ME.
HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
THE EXPERIENCE FOR IT.
ALSO, AS OF TODAY,
I AM THE NEW PALADIN.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO WORKING WITH ALL OF YOU.
HUH?
YUKIO'S THE PALADIN NOW?
SERIOUSLY?
YEP. HE'S THE DIRECTOR
OF THE JAPAN BRANCH TOO.
I KNOW, IT'S CRAZY.
MAKES ME WONDER WHAT
OUR NEW POPE'S BEEN SMOKING.
THAT SON OF A--
TYPICAL YUKIO.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
THE PALADIN FIRST, BUT HE
FREAKIN' BEAT ME TO IT.
YOU'RE GETTING ALL BENT
OUT OF SHAPE 'CAUSE OF THAT?
RIGHT. LIKE YOU EVER HAD
A CHANCE OF CATCHING UP TO ME.
YUKIO, IS WHAT
I'M HEARING TRUE?
ARE YOU REALLY
THE PALADIN NOW?
YES, I AM, JUST LIKE DAD.
OFFICIALLY, I'M THE MOST
POWERFUL EXORCIST OF ALL NOW.
YEAH, WHATEVER.
YOU RULE AND I SUCK.
YOU WORKED YOUR ASS OFF,
AND YOU'RE THE BEST LITTLE
BROTHER A GUY COULD HAVE.
THING IS,
THIS IS IMPORTANT STUFF,
SO HOW COME I'M THE LAST
TO KNOW ABOUT IT?
IT ALL HAPPENED SUDDENLY.
RIGHT, BUT YOU COULD'VE
AT LEAST TEXTED ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT. SORRY.
I'LL TRY NOT TO DO IT AGAIN.
YEAH, I CAN LIVE WITH THAT.
I WAS GIVEN THE TITLE OF PALADIN
TO SERVE ONE SPECIFIC PURPOSE--
TO GET THE BALL ROLLING
ON A MISSION
STRAIGHT FROM VATICAN H.Q.
WAIT, WHAT MISSION?
COMRADES, FOR AS LONG
AS WE CAN REMEMBER,
WE'VE LIVED IN FEAR OF DEMONS
AND THE THREAT OF ATTACK.
HOWEVER, THAT CHAPTER
OF OUR HISTORY ENDS NOW.
WE ARE THE LIGHT
THAT DRIVES OUT THE DARKNESS,
SO LET US TAKE BACK
OUR BELOVED ASSIAH.
LET US FREE MANKIND
ONCE AND FOR ALL
AND EXTERMINATE THE DEMONS.
I, POPE ERNST, HEREBY ORDER
EVERY EXORCIST IN EVERY BRANCH
THE WORLD OVER...
TO COMMENCE OPERATION
JACOB'S LADDER IMMEDIATELY.
OPERATION JACOB'S LADDER?
THE POPE CHOSE ME
TO BE THE COMMANDER
OF THE MISSION.
I CAN'T DO THIS
WITHOUT YOU, RIN,
SO WILL YOU HELP ME?
UH, YEAH.
YOU GOT IT.
I'VE GOT A MEETING.
I'LL CATCH UP
WITH YOU LATER.
GOOD LUCK.
GO GET 'EM, LITTLE BRO.
YOU'RE GIVING ME A GUN?
IT'S A GUN MADE SPECIALLY
BY THE VATICAN.
IT ABSORBS THE POWER
OF THE DEMONS YOU KILL...
AND BOOSTS YOUR EFFICIENCY
IN BATTLE.
HOLDING THIS REALLY PUTS ME
IN THE MOOD FOR SOME ACTION.
COME ON, SHIMA,
THAT'S A GUN,
NOT A TOY, OKAY?
ACTUALLY,
WE'RE IN TRAINING
TO BECOME TAMERS.
WELL, IF YOU WANT, YOU'RE FREE
TO USE THAT GRIMOIRE.
[ GASPS ]
I THINK WE'RE GOOD
WITH THESE.
EVEN THOUGH YOU'VE BEEN CLEARED
TO USE WEAPONS,
YOU DON'T HAVE EXPERIENCE
USING THEM YET.
SO BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
AND MAKE SURE THAT
WHILE YOU'RE COMPLETING
YOUR MISSIONS,
YOU DON'T GET IN THE WAY
OF THE OTHER EXORCISTS.
- [ ALL ]
YES, SIR.
- HUH?
[ GUNFIRE ]
[ SCREECHING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ ROARING ]
FOR OUR STRUGGLE
IS NOT AGAINST FLESH AND BLOOD,
BUT AGAINST THE RULERS,
AGAINST THE AUTHORITIES,
AGAINST THE POWERS
OF THIS DARK WORLD.
[ GROANS ]
[ AUTOMATIC WEAPONS FIRING ]
[ GASPS, SHOUTS ]
- [ GRUNTS ]
- SHIMA!
[ GASPING ]
[ GROANING ]
- COME ON!
- [ SCREECHES ]
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE!
FIRE!
WELL DONE, PEOPLE.
WE WON THE BATTLE FOR TODAY.
HUH?
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
IT DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT,
DOES IT?
UH, HEY, RIN, IS THIS REALLY
WHAT AN EXORCIST'S JOB IS?
I DON'T FEEL RIGHT
ABOUT THIS.
[ EGIN ]
HOW GOES IT?
[ YUKIO ]
SO FAR WE'VE PURGED
443,556 REGIONS.
HOWEVER, A FEW AREAS
STILL FACE HEAVY RESISTANCE.
JUST MAKE SURE EVERY EXORCIST
GETS THE MESSAGE--
THE ORDER IS ON A CRUSADE.
NO MATTER WHAT THE COST,
NOTHING WILL STOP US
FROM ACHIEVING OUR GOAL.
WHAT'S WRONG?
SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
NOTHING, SIR.
[ YUKIO ]
RIN CAN BE HUMAN AGAIN?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
IS THAT POSSIBLE?
IN THIS WORLD, HIS BLUE FLAMES
ARE SEALED BY KURIKARA,
BUT GEHENNA
IS WHERE THEY'RE FROM.
TWO WORLDS THAT ARE
MIRROR IMAGES OF ONE ANOTHER--
ASSIAH, THE HUMAN WORLD,
AND GEHENNA,
THE WORLD OF THE DEMONS.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS DESTROY GEHENNA.
ONCE WE DO,
HE'LL LOSE HIS DEMONIC POWER,
AND HE'LL BE HUMAN AGAIN.
DESTROY GEHENNA?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
WE DON'T HAVE THE MEANS
TO DO IT.
ACTUALLY, WE DO.
FOR THE PAST 15 YEARS,
WE'VE BEEN DEVELOPING A WEAPON
FOR THAT PURPOSE.
I CALL IT "THE MESSIAH."
IT'S READY TO LAUNCH
AT A MOMENT'S NOTICE
UPON MY ORDER.
BUT FOR NOW IT'S ON STANDBY
UNTIL WE CAN CREATE
OUR OWN GEHENNA GATE.
WHY WOULD WE NEED TO?
THE GATE SERVES
AS A SPACE-TIME PORTAL
LINKING GEHENNA AND ASSIAH.
UP TO NOW, SATAN WAS
THE ONLY ONE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO OPEN THE GEHENNA GATE.
BUT WE SUCCEEDED IN CREATING
OUR OWN VERSION.
TO KEEP IT OPEN FOR ANY LENGTH
OF TIME, THOUGH, WE NEED MASSIVE
AMOUNTS OF DEMONIC BLOOD.
AND AFTER GEHENNA
IS DESTROYED,
DO YOU REALLY THINK
MY BROTHER
WILL BECOME HUMAN?
NOT ONLY YOUR BROTHER.
YOU'LL BECOME HUMAN TOO.
[ GASPS ]
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK...
YOUR GRANDFATHER WOULDN'T KNOW
ABOUT YOUR SPECIAL PROBLEM?
HMM?
[ RIN ]
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HMM?
WHAT'S FOR DINNER?
WE WERE WONDERING
WHERE YOU WERE.
HOPE YOU LIKE
ARMY FOOD.
[ MEOWS ]
HERE. I GRABBED ONE FOR YOU
BEFORE THEY RAN OUT.
THANKS FOR HOOKING ME UP, MAN.
I WANT SOME TOO.
I WANT SOME TOO!
I KNOW.
YOU'LL GET SOME.
EVERYTHING'S 50-50 WITH US.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE HUNGRY
AFTER TODAY.
HUH?
SHIEMI?
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SNORTING ]
[ MAN #1 ]
IT'S A WILD BOAR!
[ MAN #2 ] EVACUATE!
- YUKIO?
- [ SNORTING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ BOAR ]
YOU CURSED HUMANS.
HOW DARE YOU HURT
THE CHILDREN OF MY FOREST.
FOR 2,000 YEARS
THEY'VE HELPED ME
PROTECT THIS PLACE...
FROM THE RAVAGES OF MAN.
SO HE'S THE GOD OF THIS FOREST.
- [ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
- [ GASPS ]
HEY, HOLD ON!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO--
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ GUNSHOTS CONTINUE ]
WHAT THE HELL'D
YOU DO THAT FOR, YUKIO?
WHAT? WE'RE ON A DEMON HUNT.
THAT BOAR WAS THE GOD
OF THIS FOREST.
HE WAS JUST PISSED OFF
BECAUSE WE KILLED
ALL HIS BUDDIES.
OUR ORDERS ARE CLEAR.
WE HAVE TO ERADICATE
EVERY SINGLE DEMON
OFF THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT ABOUT KURO AND UKOBACH?
WHAT ABOUT IZUMO'S
FAMILIARS, HUH?
THEY'RE DEMONS.
WHAT, YOU'RE GONNA 'EM ALL TOO?
YOU KNOW WHAT, RIN?
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
- HMM?
- WE MUST EXTERMINATE
ALL DEMONS.
STOP IT!
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ GASPS ]
[ MEOWS ]
- ARE YOU OUTTA YOUR MIND?
- YOU BETTER LET GO OF ME, RIN.
SO ANYTHING THAT CALLS ITSELF
A DEMON IS GONNA BE HUNTED DOWN
AND KILLED, IS THAT THE PLAN?
SINCE WHEN ARE EXORCISTS
MURDERERS?
I SAID LET GO OF ME!
[ GRUNTS ]
- [ GROANING ]
- RIN! WHAT DID
YOU DO TO HIM?
[ WHINING ]
[ SCREECHES ]
KURO!
[ CELL PHONE RINGS ]
OKUMURA HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
[ BEEPS ]
BOURGUIGNON?
YES, SIR.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE HIM
TO VATICAN HEADQUARTERS.
[ BOURGUIGNON ]
YES, SIR.
OKAY, SPILL IT.
YOU SAID YOUR TESTS
WERE ALL NEGATIVE.
WERE YOU LYING THIS WHOLE TIME?
WILL YOU MIND
YOUR OWN BUSINESS?
HEY, WATCH IT.
WHEN THIS MISSION IS OVER,
EVERYONE WILL BE SAVED.
I'M THE PALADIN NOW,
AND IF YOU GET IN MY WAY,
I WILL ARREST YOU.
WHO'S GETTING SAVED?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HEY!
SHIT. HE'S NOTHING
BUT A FOUR-EYED CHICKEN.
[ SUGURO ]
BLOOD-SUCKING WEAPON?
WHAT'S THAT?
[ YOSHIKUNI ]
WHAT THE NAME SAYS.
IT DRAINS THE BLOOD
OF WHATEVER IT KILLS.
I CHECKED OUT
THOSE PHOTOS YOU SENT ME.
LOOKING AT 'EM RIGHT NOW
IN FACT.
I FOUND OUT THAT
A TRANSYLVANIAN COUNT FROM
WAY BACK OWNED THOSE WEAPONS.
WHY THE HELL WOULD THEY GIVE US
WEAPONS LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE ASKING ME?
HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
ANYWAY, THESE THINGS
ARE SUPER CREEPY.
I THINK IT'S BEST
YOU STEER CLEAR OF 'EM
ALTOGETHER.
OKAY, I GOT IT.
I'M SORRY TO CALL YOU
SO EARLY IN THE MORNING.
[ BEEPS ]
[ THINKING ]
MAN, WHY DO I FEEL
LIKE THIS IS ALL WRONG?
- DAMN IT.
- UH, BON, WHERE YOU GOING?
I'M GONNA GO FIND
MR. OKUMURA.
WE NEED ANSWERS, AND SINCE
HE'S RUNNING THE SHOW NOW,
HE'S THE ONE TO ASK.
YEAH, RIGHT.
LIKE HE'S GONNA TELL US
ANYTHING.
IF YOU WANT ANSWERS,
FIND A TEACHER
WITH A BIGGER MOUTH.
OKAY, BUT WHO?
[ MIWA AND SHIEMI ]
YOU MEAN LIKE MR. TSUBAKI?
YEAH, THAT'S IT!
[ SIZZLING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ MEPHISTO ]
DID YOU SLEEP WELL?
MEPHISTO!
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE?
WE ARE IN THE BASEMENT
OF VATICAN HEADQUARTERS.
IT'S A DUNGEON
THEY CALL COCYTUS.
- CO-WHAT?
- THIS IS PROBABLY
THE LAST PLACE IN THE WORLD...
I'D EVER THINK OF SEEING YOU.
NOW WOULD YOU MIND TERRIBLY
IF I ASK...
HOW YOU MANAGED TO GET YOURSELF
LOCKED UP
IN HERE?
YOU DON'T SAY?
MR. OKUMURA IS THE NEW PALADIN?
AND THEY HAVE HIM
HUNTING DEMONS TOO.
AN INTRIGUING
TURN OF EVENTS, NO?
YEAH, I GUESS,
BUT WHY'D THEY ARREST YOU?
EINS, ZWEI, DREI.
ONCE UPON A TIME 500 YEARS AGO--
[ RIN ]
NOT SHOW-AND-TELL.
AT THE TIME, I, JOHANN FAUST,
WAS ON THE CUTTING EDGE
OF SCIENCE.
I SPECIALIZED IN THE STUDY
OF ARTIFICIAL LIFE.
SOMEONE NEEDS TO TAKE
AN ART CLASS
WHEN THEY GET OUT OF HERE.
UGH! EVERYONE'S A CRITIC.
BACK TO THE STORY.
AS YOU ALREADY KNOW,
THE VATICAN PROHIBITED
THE CREATION OF ARTIFICIAL LIFE.
HAVING LEFT MY LABORATORY
TO MY DISCIPLES A LONG TIME
BEFORE THAT DECREE,
I WAS OUT OF THE GAME.
MY DISCIPLES, HOWEVER,
CONTINUED THEIR RESEARCH.
WAIT.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT--
YE-ES.
THE RESEARCH LAB
FOR ARTIFICIAL LIFE IN POLAND.
NOIHAUS WAS MY DISCIPLE'S
DISCIPLE'S DISCI--
ANYHOO, THAT'S HOW
WE KNEW EACH OTHER.
THE END.
MR. NOIHAUS WAS SAYING
HE DIDN'T RESURRECT HIS WIFE.
HE WAS JUST KEEPING
HER BODY PRESERVED.
HE SAID SOMEONE ELSE DID IT.
NO DOUBT HE WAS FRAMED
BY THAT VERY SAME SOMEONE.
DO YOU KNOW
WHO IT IS?
FOR THE ANSWER TO THAT,
LOOK FOR THE PERSON WHO THINKS
OF ME AS THE THORN IN HIS SIDE.
THANK YOU FOR GETTING ME UP
TO SPEED WITH CURRENT EVENTS,
MY BOY.
IT HAS BEEN FUN, BUT I HAVE
TO BE SHOVING OFF NOW.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA LEAVE ME HERE?
COME ON, TAKE ME WITH YOU.
OH, I'M AFRAID NOT.
DO YOU HEAR THAT BELL SIGNALING
THE RISE OF THE CURTAIN?
THE SHOW IS ABOUT TO BEGIN,
YOU KNOW, AND ONE CANNOT AFFORD
TO MISS A SINGLE MOMENT OF IT.
ANYWAY, ARRIVEDERCI.
DON'T LEAVE ME!
YOU FRIGGIN' CLOWN!
GET YOUR FUZZY ASS BACK HERE.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
MEPHISTO'S ESCAPED,
YOUR HOLINESS.
LORD AUGUSTE.
SIR?
YOU AND BOURGUIGNON
DOUBLE THE SECURITY.
WE'RE ABOUT TO COMMENCE
WITH THE CEREMONY.
I DON'T WANT ANY DISRUPTIONS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
YES, SIR.
UNDERSTOOD.
WELL, HELLO THERE.
THAT IS REMARKABLE.
YOU LOOK EVEN MORE LIKE YURI
THAN YOUR BROTHER.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- PARDON ME.
MY NAME IS ERNST FREDRIK EGIN.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU,
MY GRANDSON.
[ SUGURO ]
EXECUTE OKUMURA?
WHY DOES HE HAVE TO DIE?
THEY NEVER SAID
ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
I HEARD HIS EXECUTION WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE ON HOLD...
UNTIL THE EXORCIST
AUTHORIZATION EXAMS
WERE THROUGH.
[ SIGHS ]
AT ANY RATE, IT'S CHAOS
AT HEADQUARTERS RIGHT NOW.
ALL THE EXORCISTS ARE ON STANDBY
UNTIL WE GET FURTHER
INSTRUCTIONS FROM THE DIRECTOR.
MR. TSUBAKI, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE KEEPING RIN
RIGHT NOW?
[ TSUBAKI ]
NO, I DON'T,
BUT I HEARD...
THE EXECUTION'S GOING
TO TAKE PLACE ON THE ROOF
OF TRUE CROSS ACADEMY.
[ SHIMA ]
THE ROOF, HUH?
[ ALL GASPING ]
I HAVE BEEN ORDERED
TO CUT DOWN ANYONE
WHO DARES TRY TO GET PAST ME.
[ GASPING ]
BASTARD. WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU GONNA DO TO ME?
[ ALL CHANTING IN LATIN ]
ECCE LIGNUM CRUCIS...
IN QUO SALUS MUNDI PEPENDIT.
VENITE ADOREMUS.
POPULE MEUS, QUID FECI TIBI?
AUT IN QUO CONTRISTAVI TE?
RESPONDE MIHI.
AGIOS O THEOS. SANCTUS DEUS.
AGIOS ISCHYROS. SANCTUS FORTIS.
AGIOS ATHANATOS, ELEISON IMAS.
SANCTUS IMMORTALIS,
MISERERE NOBIS.
ECCE LIGNUM CRUCIS...
IN QUO SALUS MUNDI PEPENDIT.
[ EGIN ]
BY CURSED DEMON BLOOD,
REVEAL WHAT IS HIDDEN.
LET THE GATES OF HELL
SWING WIDE!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
- [ GRUNTS ]
- NO!
[ ANGEL ]
THE CEREMONY
IS STILL IN PROGRESS.
YOU WILL RETURN
TO YOUR POSTS AT ONCE.
WHY THE HELL DOES THE VATICAN
WANNA EXECUTE OKUMURA?
HE HASN'T EVEN DONE ANYTHING.
THOSE WHO HAVE THE BLOOD
OF SATAN IN THEIR VEINS DESERVE
TO BE CONDEMNED TO DEATH.
BUT YOU CAN'T.
SERIOUSLY?
IS THAT WHAT THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS
CALL JUSTICE?
THE VATICAN'S ORDERS
ARE ABSOLUTE.
SINCE YOU DEFY ME,
YOU WILL BE STRUCK DOWN.
[ ALL GASPING ]
- WHOA, MISS SHURA!
- [ CHUCKLES ]
MY
WHAT A SHAME.
I NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D DEFECT
TO THE DEMONS' SIDE.
NO, I HAVEN'T DEFECTED.
BUT THE WAY YOU GUYS RUN THINGS
AROUND HERE--
THAT REALLY PISSES ME OFF
BIG TIME.
GET OUTTA HERE.
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
[ GRUNTS ]
OH, COME NOW.
IS THAT THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
BALD ASS BASTARD.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMS CONTINUE ]
[ YUKIO ]
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO MY BROTHER?
THAT SHOULD BE OBVIOUS.
HE'S BEING SACRIFICED SO THAT
I CAN OPEN THE GEHENNA GATE.
[ SCREAMING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
YOU NEVER TOLD ME THAT.
I ONLY AGREED TO THIS BECAUSE
YOU PROMISED TO MAKE RIN HUMAN.
REGARDLESS,
RIN MUST BE SACRIFICED.
HE WILL GO DOWN IN HISTORY AS
THE ONE WHO DESTROYED GEHENNA.
TODAY YOUR BROTHER DIES A HERO.
[ GASPS ]
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
[ KAMIKI ]
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON
AROUND HERE?
[ EGIN ]
BEHOLD,
THE GEHENNA GATE HAS OPENED
ON MEGIDDO HILL!
HEAR ME, SATAN, KING OF DEMONS,
USING THE WISDOM
AND TECHNOLOGY OF MANKIND,
I SHALL ANNIHILATE HELL ITSELF.
[ MEPHISTO ]
TRULY, THOSE BOYS ARE LIKE
MIRROR IMAGES OF ONE ANOTHER.
IF ONLY HE HADN'T DRAWN
THE KOMA SWORD THAT DAY,
THEIR DESTINIES WOULD HAVE
TURNED OUT DIFFERENTLY
FOR SURE.
OH, HOW THE ANTICIPATION
MAKES MY HEART GO PITTER-PAT!