[ CLINKING ]
[ BELLS TOLLING ]
YOU WANT TO KNOW MY BIRTHDAY?
YEP, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
SO WHEN IS IT?
MY BIRTHDAY IS ON MARCH 6.
MM-HMM. MM-HMM.
WHAT'S YOUR BLOOD TYPE?
B, I THINK.
UH-HUH. SHIROKU MOKUSEI.
YUP.
PISCES, TYPE B,
FIVE ELEMENTS, WOOD.
AND I HAVE YOUR RESULTS!
YOU'RE A ROMANTIC WHO LIKES TO
FOLLOW THE BEAT OF HER OWN DRUM.
YOU GOT BIG, BIG GOALS,
YOU'RE AN OPTIMIST
AND YOU LOVE TO DAYDREAM.
HUH?
OH!
HOW ABOUT YOU,
IZUMO?
MY BIRTHDAY'S OCTOBER 11,
I'M TYPE A.
AND I HAVE YOUR RESULTS!
IZUMO, YOU'RE AN IDEALIST,
AND YOU TREAT EVERYONE
FAIR AND SQUARE.
BUT EVEN THOUGH YOU PLAY NICE
WITH EVERYONE, YOU'RE ALSO
SUPER QUICK TO CRITICIZE...
ANYTHING OR ANYONE
WHO FORCES YOU
TO QUESTION YOUR OWN BELIEFS.
- RAD!
- WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT ABOUT?
THAT'S YOUR ASTROLOGICAL SIGN,
YOUR BLOOD TYPE
AND THE FOUR PILLARS OF DESTINY.
THE FORTUNE COMES OUTTA HERE.
YOUR STUDIES WOULD BENEFIT
FROM THOSE MEMORIZATION SKILLS.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAY,
BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT--
YOU'RE INTERESTED, AREN'T YA?
[ HUFFS ]
I'M OUTTA HERE.
SHE IS ONE COLD WOMAN.
DO ME.
TELL MY FORTUNE NEXT.
NOPE.
DOESN'T WORK FOR GUYS.
- HOW COME?
- I'M A SPECIALIST.
GIRL FORTUNES ONLY.
GUYS DON'T INSPIRE ME.
COME ON.
LET ME TELL YOU
MY BIRTHDAY.
I TOLD YOU,
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT BEFORE,
BUT HOW WOULD A SON OF SATAN
BE BORN?
WHO KNOWS?
[ SHIEMI SHRIEKS ]
UH, YOU OKAY?
AH, I JUST REALIZED
KAMIKI'S BIRTHDAY IS COMING UP.
♪ [ MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
SO, ANYWAY, WE'RE GOING TO THROW
A SURPRISE BIRTHDAY PARTY
FOR KAMIKI,
AND IT'LL BE
THE BEST EVER.
OF ALL THE PEOPLE,
WHY DO WE HAVE TO CELEBRATE
HER BIRTHDAY?
UH, EXCUSE ME, BON.
WE ALL VOTED FOR IT,
SO NO COMPLAINING.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO ASSIGN
EACH OF YOU A TASK.
[ ALL ]
HUH?
[ WHIMPERS ]
ONE THING BEFORE WE START.
- WHAT HAPPENS
AT PARTIES AGAIN?
- [ SHOUTING ]
THERE'S PRESENTS,
THEN THERE'S A CAKE.
AND THERE'S
ALWAYS SNACKS
AND DRINKS TOO.
AND DECORATIONS
AND STUFF.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
A PRESENT.
WHAT CAN WE GET HER
THAT SHE'LL BE SURE TO LIKE?
MEAT'S A GOOD PRESENT.
HUH?
BARBECUE, SUKIYAKI.
OH, AND ROAST BEEF TOO.
[ SIGHS ]
SO PRETTY MUCH
ALL THE STUFF
YOU WANT TO EAT?
AND OVEN-ROASTED TURKEY.
THROW THAT ON THE TABLE,
AND IT'S A PARTY.
NOT THAT I'VE EVER SEEN
OVEN-ROASTED TURKEY BEFORE.
OKUMURA, YOUR MENU'S
OUT OF CONTROL.
HEY, I THINK
A BOUQUET OF FLOWERS
WOULD BE AWESOME.
[ GIGGLES ]
THANK YOU, SHIMA.
YOU'RE SWEET.
[ KAMIKI GASPS ]
YOU CAN'T EAT FLOWERS!
RIN! THERE ARE LOTS OF FLOWERS
THAT ARE PERFECTLY EDIBLE.
IN SPRINGTIME
THERE'S ALL KINDS
OF DIFFERENT FLOWERS--
CALM DOWN, MORIYAMA.
OH, MY GOD!
WOULD YOU CUT THE CRAP ALREADY?
SHIMA, YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF THE PRESENT.
FIGURE OUT WHAT SHE WANTS,
AND GET IT BY SUNDAY.
GOTCHA.
OKUMURA, YOU'RE
ON CAKE DETAIL.
NOT BUYING IT,
BAKING IT.
YOU GOT IT.
I'VE NEVER BAKED A CAKE BEFORE,
BUT WHATEVER.
[ GROWLS ]
HUH?
KONEKOMARU,
YOU'RE IN CHARGE...
OF SHOPPING
AND OKUMURA.
HUH?
THAT LEAVES MORIYAMA AND ME
TO DECORATE THE ROOM.
[ SHIEMI ] OKAY!
[ SHIMA ]
THAT'S OUR BON.
HE'S GOT
MAD LEADERSHIP SKILLS.
UH, BON, IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I COULD DO BESIDES, UH--
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, MAN.
NO ONE KNOWS
JAPANESE SWEETS LIKE YOU,
SO WITH THOSE SKILLS,
YOU'RE GOLDEN.
BUT CAKES AND JAPANESE SWEETS
ARE COMPLETELY DIFF--
YOU SO GOT THIS.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE
A GREAT TEAM, KONEKOMARU.
UH--
SURE.
[ SUGURO ]
OKAY, PEOPLE,
IF SHE CATCHES US GETTING READY
FOR THE PARTY, IT'S OVER.
SO STAY SHARP
AND WATCH YOUR BACKS.
"PARTY" ON THREE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
[ ALL ]
PARTY!
HMM.
A BIRTHDAY PARTY.
HUH.
HUH? WHOA!
- HMM.
- OH, HI, SHIMA.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO STAND
OUT THERE.
COME ON IN.
OH, WELL,
IS PAKU AROUND?
HMM.
OH.
SHE'S BACK.
PAKU!
HUH?
HMM?
[ GASPS ]
[ GIGGLING ]
[ SHIMA HUMMING ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU GOT A MINUTE?
LET'S GO OUTSIDE.
THE WALLS HAVE EARS.
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE--
YOU KNOW?
YEAH.
[ SIGHS ]
[ SHIMA ] SORRY TO PULL YOU
OUTTA CLASS LIKE THAT.
[ PAKU ] IT'S OKAY.
AH, YOU'RE THE BEST, PAKU.
SERIOUSLY.
YOU'RE BOTH PRETTY
AND AMAZING.
[ HUFFS ]
[ MIWA ]
OKAY, OKUMURA.
READ THE RECIPE,
AND I'LL WRITE IT DOWN.
[ RIN ]
HERE GOES.
"FOUR EGGS, ONE CUP OF SUGAR,
TWO CUPS OF FLOUR,
THREE-QUARTERS"--
[ GASPS ]
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
GOOD LUCK, SOLDIER.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BLUBBERING ]
YEAH.
HUH?
WE WEREN'T DOING ANYTHING!
OOH! SEE YA!
HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH!
NOW THAT'S A DECORATION.
THIS IS AMAZING, SUGURO!
YOU'RE SO GOOD
AT DOING CRAFTS.
WELL, YEAH.
[ GASPS ]
OH, OH!
HMM?
[ GASPS ]
- WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- [ BOTH STAMMERING ]
UH--
IT'S NONE OF YOUR
BUSINESS, OKAY?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
WAIT FOR ME, SUGURO!
WHAT DID HE MEAN
BY THAT?
SO ARE YOU GOING OUT WITH HIM
OR WHAT?
WHO?
DURING LUNCH TODAY,
THE TWO OF YOU
WERE CHATTING UP A STORM.
HUH? SHIMA?
NO WAY.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YES, I SWEAR.
WE WERE JUST DISCUSSING
THE BIR--
- BIR?
- THE-THE BIRDS OF PREY.
HE WAS ASKING ME ABOUT THEM.
[ SQUAWKING ]
[ SIGHS ]
IF YOU SAY SO.
WHATEVER.
LISTEN, THAT CLOWN'S
THE WRONG GUY FOR YOU.
[ GIGGLES ]
HMM?
WHAT ARE YOU MAKING, RIN?
IT'S A BIRTHDAY CAKE.
A BIRTHDAY CAKE?
WHAT'S A CAKE?
YOU'LL SEE IN A MINUTE.
[ WHISKING ]
[ MIWA, THINKING ]
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED
THE OTHER DAY,
BEING ALONE WITH HIM IS...
REALLY AWKWARD.
[ WHISKING CONTINUES ]
OKAY, WHAT'S NEXT?
OH, RIGHT!
UH,
"SIFT THE FLOUR
AS YOU ADD IT
TO THE REST OF THE MIX."
UH, I-I-I'LL DO THAT.
AWESOME.
WAY TO SIFT.
SURE YOU NEVER BAKED
A CAKE BEFORE?
OH, I-I LEARNED IT
BY WATCHING.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, IF THIS IS
THE FIRST TIME YOU EVER BAKED
A CAKE, I COULDN'T TELL.
YOU MUST BE NATURALLY TALENTED.
OH, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
I GREW UP
IN A HOUSE FULL OF GUYS,
AND THEY ALL SUCKED AT COOKING.
I DIDN'T REALLY HAVE A CHOICE.
I HAD TO LEARN HOW TO DO IT.
OH.
READY.
COOL.
YEAH, IT'S ONE THING
IF YOU'RE COOKING FOR YOURSELF,
BUT IT'S A LOT MORE FUN
WHEN YOU COOK FOR SOMEONE ELSE,
YOU KNOW?
- THAT'S WHAT I THINK
ANYWAY.
- HMM.
YEAH, GOOD POINT.
RIGHT! GET READY TO BAKE
THE AWESOMEST CAKE EVER,
KONEKOMARU.
[ MIWA ]
DON'T STIR IT LIKE THAT!
SPONGE CAKES ARE ALL ABOUT AIR.
STIR IT GENTLY. GENTLY.
LIKE, UH, THIS?
KEEP MOVING YOUR HANDS.
YES, SIR.
[ SHIEMI HUMMING ]
[ GIGGLES ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
[ YUKIO ]
WORKING HARD?
[ GASPS ]
YUKI.
I GOT A MESSAGE
THIS MORNING...
ABOUT AN ORDER
OF MEDICINAL HERBS.
I CAME BY
TO PICK THEM UP.
HOLD ON.
I'LL GO TAKE A LOOK.
TRUE CROSS ACADEMY
DEMON PHARMACEUTICS.
UH--
ACTUALLY, I ORDERED THOSE
FOR PERSONAL USE.
REALLY?
THAT'S UNUSUAL.
LET'S SEE.
[ DRAWER OPENS ]
I HEARD ABOUT THE PARTY
YOU'RE THROWING,
AND I ALSO HEARD
THAT IT WAS YOUR IDEA.
I'M SURE KAMIKI
IS GONNA LOVE IT.
WELL, IT'S SORT OF
FOR ME TOO.
HMM?
MY GRANDMA AND MOM ALWAYS DID
SOMETHING SPECIAL FOR ME...
WHENEVER MY BIRTHDAY
CAME AROUND,
BUT I NEVER GOT TO HAVE A PARTY
WITH FRIENDS AND STUFF.
NOW THAT I'M GOING
TO THE CRAM SCHOOL,
I'VE HAD A CHANCE
TO MAKE SOME FRIENDS.
AND SO I FIGURED NOW
WAS A GOOD TIME TO GET EVERYONE
TOGETHER AND HAVE A PARTY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT'S KIND OF SELFISH, ISN'T IT?
IT'S NOT.
I THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
BY THE WAY,
WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
I MEAN, YOU AND RIN.
OH, IT'S DECEMBER THE 27TH.
HAVE YOU AND RIN EVER HAD
A BIRTHDAY PARTY BEFORE?
YES, YOU COULD SAY THAT.
SORT OF.
SORT OF HOW?
SINCE OUR BIRTHDAY
IS RIGHT AFTER CHRISTMAS,
WE'D CELEBRATE BOTH OF THEM
ON THE SAME NIGHT.
EVERYONE AT THE MONASTERY
WOULD COME TO THE PARTY.
BUT FOR SOME REASON
I NEVER CARED THAT MUCH
ABOUT MY BIRTHDAY.
HMM.
ANYWAY, I HOPE
YOUR PARTY GOES WELL.
MM-HMM.
AND IF YOU WANT,
YOU COULD COME TOO, YUKI.
I KNOW IT'LL BE REAL FUN.
[ ALL GASPING ]
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S JUST A PROTOTYPE
I WHIPPED UP.
THIS SUCKER LOOKS BADASS,
DOESN'T IT?
[ GROWLING ]
WRONG, WRONG, WRONG!
WHAT? YOU DON'T LIKE
ANGEL FOOD?
WHAT ARE YOU, BLIND?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN CHARGE OF HIM, KONEKOMARU.
I KNOW, BUT HE MADE IT
WHEN I WASN'T LOOKING.
HEY, EASE UP
ON KONEKOMARU.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT,
'CAUSE I THINK I MADE
A MASTERPIECE.
NO. YOU MADE A MISTAKE.
I DON'T SEE WHAT THE PROBLEM IS.
TO ME IT LOOKS LIKE
A PERFECTLY GOOD BIRTHDAY CAKE.
[ ALL ]
HUH?
OH, MY GOD. BIRTHDAY CAKES
AND CHRISTMAS CAKES
ARE TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
AND IT TOOK US 15 YEARS
TO REALIZE IT.
OH, RIN.
SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
WITH THIS THING?
[ RIN ]
"FROM ALL OF US
AT THE CRAM SCHOOL,
PLEASE ACCEPT THIS AS A HUMBLE
TOKEN OF OUR APPRECIATION."
[ MEPHISTO ]
A CAKE CELEBRATING
THE BIRTH OF CHRIST FOR ME?
A DEMON?
HMM. HMM.
AH.
WHOA! IT'S FANTASTIC!
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
THANKS FOR WAITING.
NO, NOT AT ALL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHOA, YOU EVEN LOOK FOXY
IN YOUR STREET CLOTHES.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- LEAD ON.
[ PANTING ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING AFTER ALL
THE WARNINGS I GAVE HER.
[ FOOTSTEPS RUNNING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
HMM?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
HUH?
OH, NO, IT'S NOTHING.
[ GIGGLES ]
SHIMA, YOU'RE WEIRD.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THIS ONE?
- YEAH, IT'S PRETTY COOL.
WATCH IT.
DON'T GET SO CLOSE.
[ GASPS ]
[ GASPING ]
I THINK IZUMO'S TRYING
TO COLLECT ALL THE FIGURES
FROM THIS SERIES.
OH, YEAH?
OH, LOOK AT THOSE BIG EYES--
SO CUTE.
SO CUTE. SO CUTE. SO CUTE.
HE SAID SHE'S CUTE!
I COULD FALL IN LOVE
WITH IT.
IN LOVE. IN LOVE. IN LOVE.
[ KAMIKI GASPS ]
IN LOVE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'VE FALLEN IN LOVE.
THEY'RE GOING WAY TOO FAST.
THEY DON'T KNOW EACH OTHER
THAT WELL.
WHERE'D THEY GO?
[ PANTING ]
UH-OH, IT'S RAINING.
AW, DARN IT.
I DIDN'T BRING
AN UMBRELLA ALONG TODAY.
HAVE NO FEAR.
I'VE GOT JUST WHAT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
[ GASPS ]
THEY'RE SHARING AN UMBRELLA!
OH.
OH, WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, SOMETHING GOT
IN MY EYE, IS ALL.
HERE, LET ME SEE.
[ SHRIEKING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
NO! NO!
[ GASPS ]
[ KAMIKI SHRIEKING ]
THERE. I GOT IT.
WHOA!
[ GROANS ]
I-IZUMO?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
[ BOTH ]
UH--
GUESS SHE CAUGHT US.
[ LAUGHS ]
I WASN'T TRYING TO CATCH ANYONE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
TRYING TO KISS PAKU
IN THE MIDDLE...
OF THE STREET...
WHERE EVERYONE CAN SEE?
HUH? I WASN'T TRYING
TO KISS HER.
HE WASN'T TRYING
TO KISS ME.
THEN WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
SNEAKING AROUND?
WE WEREN'T SNEAKING AROUND.
WE WERE TRYING TO FIND
A BIRTHDAY PRES...
ENT.
[ THUNDERCLAP ]
I SWEAR IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I SORTA LET THE CAT
OUT OF THE BAG.
NICE JOB, YOU DUMBASS.
WAY TO GO.
I'M SORRY.
BUT I DON'T GET IT.
WHY ARE YOU MAD?
YOU HANG ME OUT TO DRY
LIKE THIS?
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA LET
YOU GET AWAY WITH IT.
[ SUGURO ]
CHILL OUT.
NO ONE'S HANGING ANYTHING.
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE USING ME AS AN EXCUSE
JUST SO YOU CAN ALL GO HAVE FUN.
BUT, IZUMO,
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY.
WE'RE DOING THIS FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I SAID WE SHOULD THROW YOU
A BIRTHDAY PARTY,
AND I WANTED IT
TO BE A SURPRISE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE APOLOGIZING.
YOU KNOW, MORIYAMA WORKED HARD
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
SO WHAT'S WITH THE ATTITUDE?
IS IT REALLY SUCH A DRAG
THAT EVERYONE WANTS TO CELEBRATE
YOUR BIRTHDAY?
NO. IT'S NOT A DRAG.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
[ SUGURO ]
THEN WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I'M JUST SAYING
IT'S UNFAIR, IS ALL.
[ ALL ]
UNFAIR?
ALL THESE MONTHS GO BY,
AND NOW YOU WANT TO THROW
A PARTY FOR ME?
HOW UNFAIR IS THAT?
WHAT ABOUT
EVERYONE ELSE'S BIRTHDAYS?
HOW MANY HAVE WE SKIPPED
SINCE THE FIRST DAY
OF CLASS, HUH?
[ ALL GASP ]
I'M SURE A COUPLE OF YOU
TURNED 16 BY NOW.
AM I WRONG?
THE OTHER DAY, YOU GUYS
WERE TALKING ABOUT GETTING
YOUR MOTORCYCLE LICENSES.
I GOTTA HAND IT
TO YOU, IZUMO.
YOU'RE SHARP.
THERE, SEE?
I KNEW IT.
IF YOU WANT TO THROW A PARTY,
LET'S DO IT RIGHT AND CELEBRATE
EVERYONE'S BIRTHDAY.
OTHERWISE, YOU CAN
FORGET ABOUT MINE.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
THEN IT'LL BE BON'S
AND SHIMA'S AND KAMIKI'S.
PAKU'S TOO.
THAT MEANS WE'LL HAVE TO GET
FOUR BIRTHDAY PRESENTS.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
IT'S FAIR FOR EVERYONE,
SO WE'LL GIVE BACK SUGURO
AND SHIMA'S MONEY.
THEN-- THEN---
MAN, IS THIS GONNA BE
A PAIN IN THE BUTT.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK
ABOUT INCLUDING PEOPLE WHOSE
BIRTHDAYS ARE COMING UP SOON?
YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE THAT WAY
WE CAN CELEBRATE
EVERYONE'S BIRTHDAY TOGETHER.
[ GASPS ]
I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO SPELL THIS.
NO WORRIES.
I CAN SPELL IT FOR YOU.
YOU READY?
UH, H-A-P-P-Y.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S DONE.
SO DOES
EVERYONE
HAVE SOMETHING TO DRINK?
MM-HMM.
[ RIN ]
IT'S READY!
HEY, HURRY UP. WE'RE HUNGRY.
DID YOU BAKE THAT CAKE
BY YOURSELF?
YEAH, I COULDN'T DO
ANYTHING ELSE 'CAUSE COOKING'S
THE ONLY PRODUCTIVE SKILL I GOT.
[ LAUGHS ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE ADMITTED THAT.
[ ALL GASPING ]
FLASH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
KONEKOMARU!
[ GROANS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
THANKS A LOT.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SHIEMI ]
THREE, TWO--
[ ALL ]
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
[ SHIMA ]
THIS IS THE MOMENT
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
TIME FOR PRESENTS.
YOU WON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING TILL YOU'VE DRAWN
A NUMBER FROM THE BOX.
SO WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
OH, ME! I WILL!
I'LL GO FIRST.
[ GIGGLING ]
IS EVERYTHING OKAY, YUKI?
SURE. EVERYONE LOOKS
LIKE THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU HAVING FUN TOO?
OF COURSE I AM.
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
SO STRANGE LATELY.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
AS KIDS, RIN AND I
WERE ALWAYS TOLD OUR BIRTHDAYS
WERE ON DECEMBER THE 27TH.
BUT IT NEVER SEEMED REAL TO US.
COME ON, PICK NUMBER ONE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHEN WE WERE
REALLY BORN OR WHERE.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO OUR MOTHER WAS.
- ALL RIGHT!
- HUH?
[ YOUNG RIN ]
COME ON, DAD,
TELL US ABOUT MOM.
WHAT WAS SHE LIKE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I PICKED YOU GUYS UP
UNDER A BRIDGE.
OH, NOT AGAIN.
IT'S THE TRUTH. IT WAS WINTER,
AND A WATERMELON THIS BIG
CAME FLOATING DOWN THE RIVER.
AND WHEN I SPLIT
THAT SUCKER OPEN, I FOUND
THE TWO OF YOU INSIDE IT.
FOR REALS?
YEAH, I REMEMBER
THERE WAS ALL THIS TALK...
ABOUT WHETHER I SHOULD SLICE IT
VERTICALLY OR HORIZONTALLY.
IF I CUT INTO THAT MELON
THE WRONG WAY OR IF I WAS OFF
A BIT, I'D WHACK YOU IN HALF.
AW, COME ON, DAD!
[ YUKIO ]
MY FATHER ALWAYS EVADED
THE SUBJECT,
AND HE NEVER TOLD US
THE TRUTH ABOUT HER.
HE CAME CLOSE ONCE.
[ GASPING ]
[ FUJIMOTO ]
THE FIRST TIME I MET YOU BOYS
IT WAS SNOWING, JUST LIKE TODAY.
HUH?
BUT THAT WAS THE ONLY CLUE
WE EVER GOT FROM HIM.
AND NOW THAT HE'S GONE,
RIN AND I HAVE NO WAY...
OF EVER FINDING OUT
WHEN OUR REAL BIRTHDAY IS.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
- HE'S SO CUTE!
- THAT'S HILARIOUS.
YUKI?
HMM?
I'M REALLY GLAD YOU WERE BORN.
[ GASPS ]
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHERE
IT HAPPENED OR WHEN.
I'M HAPPY YOU'RE HERE
EITHER WAY.
THANKS, SHIEMI.
[ SHIMA ]
HEY, YOU GUYS!
HURRY UP AND PICK ONE.
YOU'VE GOT NUMBER TWO
OR NUMBER SEVEN.
LET'S GO.
[ SIGHS ]
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ LAUGHING ]
NICE GLASSES, GUY!
THEY'RE PERFECT!
[ SIGHS ]
[ CELL PHONE VIBRATES ]
[ CHATTERING ]
YES. OKUMURA SPEAKING.
[ CHATTERING CONTINUES ]
WHAT?
YES. RIGHT.
UNDERSTOOD.
I'M ON THE WAY.
- WHAT'S GOING ON, YUKIO?
- IT'S ABOUT OUR MONASTERY.
HUH?
IT'S BEEN ATTACKED.
[ GASPS ]
[ RIN ]
I'M NOT GONNA LET ANYONE ELSE
GET HURT 'CAUSE OF ME.
THIS IS MY FIGHT TOO,
SO I'M GOING.
[ YUKIO ]
YOU'RE NOT, AND THAT'S THAT.
[ SHURA ]
HEY, YUKIO, WHY ARE YOU
FREAKING OUT LIKE THAT?
[ YUKIO ]
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
REVENGE?