[FEMALE GRIGORI]
HE MOVED.
DON'T TELL ME
THAT DEMON'S WAKING UP.
WE CAN'T ALLOW THAT.
SIR PHELES,
DO SOMETHING IMMEDIATELY.
IF YOU RECALL, I'M THE DEFENDANT
IN THIS COURTROOM.
IT WOULD BE UNETHICAL IF I WERE
TO GO ABOUT TAMPERING WITH
THE EVIDENCE AGAINST ME.
HOWEVER, IF YOU
REALLY WANT ME TO,
ALL I'D NEED FROM THE COURT
IS THE FOLLOWING ORDER--
RELEASE THE SON OF SATAN,
AND USE HIM AS A WEAPON
TO PROTECT THE VATICAN.
[RUMBLING]
[EXPLOSION]
[SQUEAKING]
[THUNDERING FOOTSTEPS]
[AMAIMON]
I CAN SMELL HIM.
THE SCENT OF RIN OKUMURA.
[SHOUTING]
AH, HE'S OVER THERE.
- HUH?
- [GROWLING]
FOR YOUR SAFETY,
STAY BACK, MY LADY.
AH, SHUT UP,
YOU HIPPIE!
CALIBAN, LEND ME YOUR POWER.
REALLY, ARTHUR, YOU'RE SUCH
A SLAVE DRIVER.
[GRUNTS]
KIRIGAKURE SWORD TECHNIQUE,
SNAKE BELLY FORM.
SNAKE FANG!
[ROARING]
[GASPS]
HOW DARE YOU.
YOU KILLED MY BEHEMOTH!
[RUMBLING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS]
I FOUND YOU.
[LAUGHING]
[SHOUTING]
NO PRESSURE, BUT THE POLLS
WILL BE CLOSING SOON.
TIME TO CAST YOUR VOTES--
YEA OR NAY.
YOU FIEND!
YOU CAME KNOWING FULL WELL
THIS WOULD HAPPEN, DIDN'T YOU?
THIS WAS ALL A PLOY.
YOU KNEW SATAN'S SPAWN
WOULD ATTRACT ANOTHER DEMON.
I'M SURE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
INSTEAD OF OVERANALYZING
THE SITUATION, SHOULDN'T YOU
BE PROTECTING THE GRIGORI...
AND NOT POINTING
YOUR LIVE LITTLE FINGER AT ME?
I'VE COME TO SETTLE THINGS,
RIN OKUMURA.
[EXPLOSION]
YOU LITTLE PEST!
STICK AROUND.
AFTER THIS, I'LL COME AND KILL
EACH ONE OF YOU TOO.
ENOUGH, SIR PHELES.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT METHODS YOU EMPLOY.
EXTERMINATE THAT DEMON AT ONCE.
YOUR WISH IS MY COMMAND.
OKUMURA!
YOU GONNA SLEEP ALL DAY?
WAKE THE HELL UP!
[SLOW, THUNDEROUS POUNDING]
IS THAT--
KURIKARA.
THEY WERE ABLE TO FIX IT.
I CAN HEAR IT--
RIN OKUMURA'S HEARTBEAT.
GIVE ME THAT SWORD!
SHIMA!
WHAT THE--
BAD IDEA.
[GROANS]
CATCH!
WHAT?
DON'T THROW IT TO ME.
- [YUKIO]
OVER HERE, KAMIKI.
- CATCH!
YUKIO!
TEACH!
[GROANING]
COME ON.
WAKE UP, RIN.
WAKE UP!
THE BLUE FLAMES.
THEY'RE AS BRIGHT
AS THEY WERE
THAT NIGHT.
[CHUCKLING]
[RIN THINKING]
WHERE AM I?
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
I CAN'T FEEL ANYTHING.
AM I DEAD?
NO.
I CAN HEAR IT.
THAT'S MY--
MY HEART.
I'LL CRUSH YOU!
I'M NOT DEAD... YET.
IMPOSSIBLE.
I AM KING OF EARTH.
HOW COULD I LOSE?
HOW COULD I EVER LOSE?
BROTHER!
[YUKIO]
RIN!
[SHIEMI]
HEY, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
I'M GOING TO SEVER
THE BLOODLINE OF SATAN.
STAND DOWN, ANGEL.
WE'VE DECIDED TO ACCEPT
THE WAGER PROPOSED
BY SIR PHELES.
WHETHER HE BECOMES
THE SAVIOR OF ASSIAH,
OR HE BECOMES THE DEMON
WHO DESTROYS IT,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE NOW
BUT TO WAIT AND SEE.
♪ [MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[MEPHISTO]
I SUPPOSE
YOU'RE ALL WONDERING...
WHY I'VE ASKED YOU HERE
ON THIS FINE DAY.
WE'VE JUST RECEIVED
AN ORDER FROM THE VATICAN.
AS OF TODAY, RIN OKUMURA,
WHO HAPPENS TO BE
THE SON OF SATAN,
WILL BECOME OUR CHARGE
AT TRUE CROSS ACADEMY.
- QUESTIONS?
- SIR?
YES, MR. YUNOKAWA.
THERE'S BEEN TALK
ABOUT THE FOREST FIRE
THAT BROKE OUT,
AND THAT IT HAPPENED
BECAUSE OKUMURA LOST CONTROL
OF HIS POWER.
- ARE WE IN ANY DANGER HERE?
- I CAN'T SAY FOR CERTAIN
YOU AREN'T.
THAT BEING THE CASE,
IF THE BOY SHOULD HAPPEN
TO GO BERSERK AGAIN
FOR ANY REASON,
WE HAVE ORDERS
TO EXTERMINATE HIM.
- [MURMURING]
- THIS SOUNDS FAR TOO RISKY.
WOULDN'T HE BE BETTER OFF
SOMEWHERE ELSE?
I MEAN, IS THERE A REASON
WE HAVE TO TAKE HIM IN?
OH, MY, THERE'S NO REASON.
[ALL]
WHAT?
THERE'S A TON OF POTENTIAL
BUBBLING IN RIN OKUMURA,
AND I'M BETTING
ON WHETHER OR NOT
WE'LL SEE HIM LIVE UP TO IT.
[WARBLING]
[YUKIO]
SIR PHELES.
- YES?
- YOU SPOKE
OF MY BROTHER'S POTENTIAL.
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
HE'LL BECOME
THE SAVIOR OF ASSIAH?
I HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO BELIEVE IT.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO CONVINCE THE VATICAN
OF THE VALUE OF RIN'S LIFE.
IT'S A RECKLESS WAGER.
THE GRIGORI HAVE ISSUED
TWO CONDITIONS...
WHICH WE MUST ADHERE TO
BY ANY AND ALL MEANS POSSIBLE.
FIRST, WE MUST ENSURE HE PASSES
THE EXORCIST AUTHORIZATION EXAM
IN SIX MONTHS' TIME.
IMPOSSIBLE.
SECOND, TO SAFEGUARD
AGAINST POTENTIAL
FLARE-UPS,
WE MUST KEEP HIM
UNDER 24-HOUR SURVEILLANCE.
I SAY "WE,"
BUT ACTUALLY
THAT DUTY IS YOURS.
ALONG WITH MS. KIRIGAKURE.
THAT IS IMPOSSIBLE.
EVEN SO,
THERE'S NO CHOICE
BUT TO PLAY THIS OUT.
THE GAME HAS ALREADY BEGUN,
HAS IT NOT, GOOD SIR?
[WARBLING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
CAN'T COUNT ON ANYONE, CAN I?
[YOSHIKUNI]
I DID THE BEST I COULD
TO FIX IT FOR NOW.
HOWEVER, I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN FIX IT AGAIN.
IF YOU ASK ME,
SEALING A DEMON'S POWER
IN KURIKARA IS CRAZY.
SO IF IT GETS DAMAGED AGAIN,
IT WON'T BE COVERED
UNDER MY WARRANTY.
THE KOMA SWORD WAS FORGED
BY MY ANCESTORS...
AND USED AGAINST THE DEMONS
THAT TERRORIZED KYOTO LONG AGO.
PLEASE TAKE GOOD CARE OF IT.
[KURO]
RIN, IT'S GETTING LATE.
HUH?
OH, CRAP.
HOLD THE FORT DOWN
FOR ME, OKAY?
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
[SHIMA]
THIS SUCKS.
WHY ARE THEY MAKING US DO THIS
ON THE LAST DAY
OF SUMMER VACATION?
QUIT WHINING
AND START SWINGING
THAT NET, SHIMA.
KONEKOMARU,
WE'RE GOOD HERE.
I THINK MAYBE MORIYAMA
MIGHT NEED YOUR HELP MORE.
OKAY.
OH. NO, WE'RE FINE.
WE CAN HANDLE IT.
I BET YOUR ARM
STILL HURTS.
WHY DON'T YOU RELAX
FOR A BIT?
UH, SURE.
I'LL TAKE A BREAK TOO.
NO, YOU NEED
TO WORK HARDER.
BUT I SORT OF GOT HIT
IN THE RIBS, REMEMBER?
SO---
WHAT UP, GUYS?
[GASPS]
- HUH?
- GOOD MORNING, RIN.
UH, MORNING.
I STOPPED BY THE CLASSROOM
OUT OF HABIT, BUT YOU GUYS
WEREN'T THERE.
I SORTA GOT FREAKED OUT.
SO WE'RE EXTERMINATING
COAL TARS?
MAN, THEY LOVE STICKING US
WITH THESE LAME JOBS,
DON'T THEY?
ANYONE GOT
AN EXTRA DUST RAG?
I DON'T. UH, MAYBE
THERE'S ONE OVER THERE.
I'LL TAKE OUT
THE GARBAGE.
- I CAN GIVE YOU A HAND
WITH THAT.
- NO. I CAN DO IT MYSELF.
UH, HEY, WAIT UP, MAN.
[GASPS]
[KAMIKI]
OH, HE'S BEING A CHICKEN...
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE CHILD
OF A DEMON,
AND NOT JUST ANY DEMON,
BUT SATAN,
WHO IN ONE NIGHT
SLAUGHTERED EXORCISTS
THE WORLD OVER.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOU EXPOSE...
YOUR TRUE NATURE
AND BECOME A THREAT.
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[HUFFS]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[CRASHING]
[SHRIEKS]
MORIYAMA?
[RIN]
SHIEMI!
[SUGURO]
THEY'RE IN THE AIR DUCTS!
DON'T BREATHE.
YOUR LUNGS WILL ROT
IF THEY GET IN.
GET THE HELL AWAY FROM HER!
[SHIEMI SCREAMING]
OH, MORIYAMA!
HUH? HE'S NOT HOT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
YOU TRYING TO BURN HER ALIVE
OR SOMETHING.
HUH?
THOSE BLUE FLAMES OF YOURS
KILL PEOPLE.
MY GRANDPA.
SHIMA'S OLDEST BROTHER.
KONEKOMARU'S
MOM AND DAD.
THEY WERE ALL KILLED
THE SAME WAY
BY YOUR FATHER, SATAN!
UH--
OH.
[MIWA]
SIXTEEN YEARS AGO, SATAN
CROSSED THE BARRIER...
TO OUR WORLD AND MASSACRED
ALL THE TOP CLERGYMEN.
WE'VE CALLED IT
THE BLUE NIGHT EVER SINCE.
[RIN, THINKING]
SO THAT NIGHT,
THEIR FAMILIES WERE KILLED TOO?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE VATICAN
DECIDED TO DO WITH YOU,
BUT AS OF RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE NOT YOUR FRIENDS ANYMORE.
[GASPS]
I'M WARNING YOU.
IF YOU GO NUTS AND HURT
EVEN ONE OF MY FRIENDS,
I SWEAR I'LL KILL YOU.
YOU GOT THAT?
BUT I--
I'M NOT GONNA BE LIKE SATAN.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST ME.
[YUKIO]
ALL RIGHT.
ENOUGH.
YUKIO.
OKUMURA, YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE STARTING
A NEW CURRICULUM TODAY.
AND AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
PLEASE CONTINUE YOUR WORK.
[GASPS]
HEY! I'M NOT DONE
TALKING YET.
- RIN.
- LET GO,
YOU FOUR-EYED MOLE FACE.
DAMN IT.
WHY DO I HAVE TO TAKE
THESE CLASSES BY MYSELF?
LOOK, YOU DON'T HAVE TIME
TO SCREW AROUND ANYMORE.
UNTIL YOU QUALIFY
AS AN EXORCIST,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
IN SERIOUS TRAINING MODE.
SO YOU BETTER
GET USED TO IT.
- WHAT THE HELL IS ALL THIS?
SOME KIND OF BATTING CAGE?
- [BEEPING]
[COMPUTERIZED WOMAN'S VOICE]
YOU HAVE SELECTED
BEGINNER'S MODE.
ARE YOU LISTENING,
RIN?
[SIGHS]
YOU HAVE SIX MONTHS TO PASS
THE EXORCIST AUTHORIZATION EXAM.
YEAH, I KNOW.
OR THEY'RE GONNA KILL ME.
[BEEPING]
TRAINING WILL NOW BEGIN.
AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I BET I CAN PASS THE EXAM...
WITHOUT HAVING TO DO
ALL THIS TRAINING CRAP ANYWAY.
I'VE ALREADY ANNIHILATED A
BOATLOAD OF DEMONS, SO I'M SET.
OH, YEAH?
WASN'T THAT JUST DUMB LUCK?
DUMB?
[SHOUTS]
[GROANING]
YOU JUST TOLD SUGURO
TO TRUST YOU.
OR WAS I HEARING THINGS?
SO? WHAT IF I DID?
[GASPS]
IF YOU WANNA EARN
SOMEONE'S TRUST, YOU HAVE
TO PROVE YOURSELF TO THEM.
AND THE WAY THINGS ARE,
YOU'VE GOT A LOT LEFT TO PROVE
TO EVERYONE.
YEAH? LIKE WHAT?
[SHURA]
THE FOUR-EYED CHICKEN'S
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
[YUKIO]
SHURA.
[RIN]
WHAT'S WITH THAT OUTFIT?
IT'S CALLED ECO FRIENDLY.
[THINKING]
ECO FRIENDLY? YOU JUST
SHOWED UP IN YOUR PAJAMAS.
SINCE YOU'RE THE SPAWN OF SATAN
AND ALL, YOU'RE KINDA LIKE
A DEMONIC THOROUGHBRED.
THE ONLY REASON YOU MANAGED
TO GET BY TILL NOW IS 'CAUSE OF
ALL THAT UNTAPPED POTENTIAL.
THAT'S IT.
AND EVEN WITH
ALL THAT POTENTIAL,
YOU STILL HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO CONTROL THOSE POWERS.
TILL THEN, YOU GOT NO CHANCE
OF BECOMING AN EXORCIST,
NEVER MIND A PALADIN.
WELL, THEN WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
TRAIN YOUR ASS OFF,
NATCH.
- HERE.
- [GASPS]
A CANDLE?
DUH. OKAY, FIRST, LINE UP
THREE OF THOSE CANDLES
SIDE BY SIDE,
AND TRY TO LIGHT THE ONES
ON EACH END
AT THE SAME TIME.
GOT IT.
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
LIGHT THEM, NOT ENGULF THEM
IN YOUR UNGODLY HELL FIRE.
YEAH, I'LL TRY IT AGAIN.
REALLY?
UH, THAT'S THE MIDDLE ONE,
DUMBASS.
I SAID LIGHT 'EM
AT THE SAME TIME.
- [SHOUTING]
- YOU'RE SO SLOPPY,
SLOPPY DOESN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO DESCRIBE YOU.
BUT THIS IS REALLY HARD.
BOO-FRICKIN'-HOO.
YOU'RE DOING THREE SETS A DAY
FOR AN HOUR EACH.
I WANT YOU TO KEEP AT IT
TILL YOU CAN DO IT EVEN WHILE
YOU'RE PICKING YOUR NOSE.
HUH?
THAT'S MY TRAINING?
WH-WHAT ABOUT MY SWORD?
[SIGHS]
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA...
WHY YOU LOST CONTROL OF YOURSELF
DURING YOUR FIGHT WITH AMAIMON?
UH-UH.
NOT A CLUE.
YOU LOST IT 'CAUSE YOU CHICKENED
OUT, THAT'S WHY.
IT'S WHY YOUR FLAMES
CONSUME YOU.
GET USED TO YOUR FLAMES,
BUILD UP YOUR CONFIDENCE.
THEN WE CAN TALK
ABOUT THE KOMA SWORD.
[THINKING]
IT PISSES ME OFF,
BUT SHE'S RIGHT, DAMN IT.
OKAY. I GOT THIS.
[GASPS, GROANS]
I WONDER IF THE KID'S
EVER GONNA GET IT.
[RIN GRUNTING]
HUH?
YOU LOOK ALL GLOOMY
AS USUAL.
YOU KNOW, YOU KEEP HANGING ON
TO THAT STRESS,
YOU'RE GONNA GET AN ULCER.
AND WHOSE FAULT WOULD THAT BE?
I GOT AN IDEA,
MR. FOUR-EYED CHICKEN.
HOW ABOUT WE TAKE THE EDGE OFF
EXORCIST STYLE?
- PASS.
- HOLY CRAP, THAT WAS FAST.
YOU'RE SO ANTISOCIAL.
REMEMBER THE DAYS
WE USED TO BET EACH OTHER LUNCH
ON THESE MATCHES?
WHOO-HOO!
SIXTEEN WINS IN A ROW
FOR ME!
[LAUGHING]
[GROANS]
HEY, SHURA, IT'S NOT COOL
TO GO ALL OUT
AGAINST A MIDDLE SCHOOLER.
RELAX. I WAS JUST SHOWING HIM
HOW BRUTAL THE COMPETITION
CAN BE IN THE REAL WORLD.
YO, CHICKEN, YOU LOST TODAY,
SO YOU'RE BUYING ME LUNCH
TOMORROW.
OKAY, WHATEVER.
JUST STOP CALLING ME
CHICKEN ALREADY.
[LAUGHS]
YOU KNOW, YUKIO,
YOU'RE TOTALLY GETTING
PLAYED BY HER.
- BULLSHIT.
- [GASPS]
DID YOU JUST SAY "BULLSHIT"?
UNBELIEVABLE.
I REALLY DON'T LIKE THAT GIRL
ONE BIT.
SHE'S GOT ALL THAT TALENT,
BUT SHE'S ALWAYS SLACKING OFF.
SHE MAKES ME FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT
FOR STUDYING SO HARD.
THERE'S TWO SIDES
TO EVERY STORY, SON.
EVEN THOUGH SHE DOESN'T ACT
LIKE IT, SHE WORKS HER BUTT OFF
JUST LIKE YOU.
OKAY, I'M IN.
HOWEVER,
IF I WIN, YOU HAVE TO STOP
CALLING ME "FOUR-EYED CHICKEN,"
YOU GOT THAT?
HMM. SURE.
SAME RULES AS BEFORE.
WE ROCK INFINITY MODE,
AND THE FIRST ONE
WHO LOSES THEIR CONCENTRATION
LOSES THE BET.
SOUND GOOD?
I CAN LIVE WITH THAT.
[BEEPING]
YOU HAVE SELECTED
SPECIAL INFINITY MODE.
TRAINING WILL NOW BEGIN.
HOLY CRAP!
THOSE THINGS
ARE GOING SO FAST,
BUT THEY'RE SMASHING
EVERY ONE OF 'EM
LIKE IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
THOSE GUYS ARE MACHINES.
WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
GO FOCUS ON YOUR CANDLES, KID.
ACTUALLY, SHURA,
YOU SHOULD BE THE ONE FOCUSING.
DON'T GIVE ME YOUR LIP, CHICKEN.
KEEP SHOOTING.
HE'S BEHIND THE PILLAR
ON THE SOUTH SIDE
OF THE TRAINING ROOM.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S KEEPING HIMSELF
HIDDEN, YOU CAN SEE HIM, YEAH?
- IS HE WORKING
FOR THE VATICAN?
- UH-HUH.
BUT RIN'S NOT THE ONLY ONE
HE'S KEEPING AN EYE ON.
- HE'S WATCHING YOU.
- WHY WOULD THE GRIGORI
DO THAT?
THEY ORDERED ME TO WATCH RIN.
THEY TRUST ME.
[SHURA]
BUT YOU'RE THE SON OF SATAN TOO.
TO THE VATICAN, YOU'RE AS MUCH
OF A THREAT TO THEM
AS YOUR BROTHER.
I'M NOTHING LIKE MY BROTHER.
IN CASE YOU HADN'T NOTICED,
I DON'T HAVE HIS POWERS.
IF YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT,
HOW COME YOU GET YOURSELF
CHECKED OUT EVERY DAY?
IT'S 'CAUSE YOU'RE AFRAID,
THAT'S WHY.
YOU THINK THE DAY IS GONNA COME
WHEN YOU'LL FIND YOURSELF WITH
THE SAME DEMONIC POWER AS RIN.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
- OR MAYBE IT'S
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
MAYBE YOU WANNA HAVE THAT POWER
ALL FOR YOURSELF.
NICE TRY, BUT YOU CAN'T
DISTRACT ME BY MESSING
WITH MY HEAD LIKE THAT.
I HOPE THAT'S TRUE.
WATCH OUT.
YOU'RE THE TYPE WHO GETS
POSSESSED BY DEMONS EASY.
I CAN TELL.
WHAT?
[THINKING]
IS THAT HOW GOOD
A PRO'S SUPPOSED TO BE?
MAN, IT TOOK EVERYTHING I HAD
JUST TO HIT A COUPLE OF THEM
IN BEGINNER MODE.
[GRUNTS]
SHIT!
- WHAT THE HELL?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
[STAMMERING]
UH--
WHY DID YOU DO THIS
TO US, RIN?
HUH? SORRY. MY BAD.
HOLD UP THOUGH.
YOUR CLOTHES BURNED OFF,
BUT NOT YOUR UNDERWEAR OR SKIN.
YOU SEE? THAT PROVES
I CAN CONTROL MY POWER.
THE HELL YOU CAN.
YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
[GIGGLES]
I'LL GET
THE HOLY WATER.
THANKS.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
[SUGURO]
FOR BY HIM,
ALL THINGS WERE CREATED.
THINGS IN HEAVEN
AND ON EARTH--
STILL STUDYING?
SORRY ABOUT THAT, MAN.
DIDN'T MEAN TO WAKE YOU.
I JUST GOT UP
TO USE THE RESTROOM.
YOU SHOULD TRY TO GET
SOME SLEEP, THOUGH,
OR YOU'LL BURN YOURSELF OUT.
BUT I DON'T WANNA LOSE.
[GASPS]
TO WHOM? KAMIKI?
NO, YOU DUMMY.
I MEAN TO OKUMURA.
YOU'RE WAY AHEAD OF HIM.
YOU'RE THE TOP STUDENT...
IN PHARMACOLOGY
AND SCRIPTURE RECITATION.
YEAH, BUT STRAIGHT A'S
AREN'T GONNA HELP ANYONE
IN REAL-WORLD COMBAT.
[SIGHS]
THAT HIT HOME
AFTER OUR CAMPING TRIP.
[SIGHS]
BON--
I PROMISE I'M GONNA BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED EXORCIST
AS SOON AS I CAN.
OTHERWISE I WON'T BE ABLE
TO HOLD MY HEAD UP
TO YOUR MOM AND DAD.
[MIWA]
RIGHT.
BON IS SO STRONG.
EVEN AFTER WHAT WE SAW,
HE STILL THINKS OKUMURA
IS HIS RIVAL,
WHILE I CAN'T EVEN BE
IN THE SAME ROOM AS HE IS.
[MALE VOICE]
ARE YOU AFRAID?
[GASPS]
YOU'LL END UP
LOSING THEM AGAIN--
YOUR LOVED ONES;
THOSE DEAR TO YOU.
NOW THEN,
ACCEPT ME.
WHO ARE YOU?
ACCEPT THIS FEAR.
[GASPS]
[RIN GRUNTING]
OH, COME ON, MAN!
WHY CAN'T I MAKE IT DO
WHAT I WANT IT TO?
OH, I GUESS I DON'T HAVE
THE TALENT FOR IT.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
UH, WHO'S THERE?
IT'S ME WONDERING WHY
YOU'RE SITTING THERE
TALKING TO YOURSELF.
I WASN'T.
ANYWAY, WHY ARE YOU SNEAKING
AROUND HERE THIS EARLY
IN THE MORNING?
I'M NOT SNEAKING.
I JUST FORGOT
MY PENCIL CASE.
UH-- OH.
WHAT KIND OF TRAINING
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
OH. I HAVE TO LIGHT THE CANDLES
ON THE ENDS,
NOT THE ONE IN THE MIDDLE,
BUT IT'S NOT WORKING OUT
SO HOT FOR ME.
THAT REMINDS ME.
REMEMBER WHEN PAKO
GOT ATTACKED BY THAT GHOUL?
YEAH.
DURING THAT BOOT CAMP THING.
THAT DAY MY FAMILIARS
WOULDN'T OBEY ME
BECAUSE I WAS SCARED.
I LOST MY CONFIDENCE.
AND I LOST CONTROL.
YOUR FLAMES WORK THE SAME WAY.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
BE CONFIDENT, AND I'M SURE
THEY'LL OBEY YOU.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
HEY, WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
WHAT?
YOU GAVE ME GOOD ADVICE.
WHY'D YOU GO OUT OF YOUR WAY
TO TELL ME ALL THAT STUFF?
I MEAN, AREN'T YOU SCARED OF ME
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE?
NOT REALLY.
I GUESS YOU
DIDN'T KNOW THIS,
BUT ACTUALLY
IT'S NOT THAT UNUSUAL...
FOR DEMONS AND HUMANS
TO HAVE BLOOD TIES
WITH EACH OTHER.
AND FOR EXORCISTS,
IT'S PRETTY COMMON.
[GASPS]
NO WAY.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
EVERYONE KNOWS THAT.
AND NOW THAT YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE ALL MOPEY
AND STRESS OUT ABOUT
YOUR BLOODLINE ANYMORE.
IF PEOPLE WANNA MAKE
A BIG DEAL OUT OF IT,
THEN YOU CAN... TELL 'EM--
THANKS, POLKA BROW!
HUH?
YOU'RE A PRETTY RAD PERSON
AFTER ALL.
YOU CALLED ME POLKA BROW?
DON'T YOU GIVE ME
WEIRD NICKNAMES.
I HAVE A PROPER NAME.
IT'S IZUMO KAMIKI, GOT THAT?
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT, IZUMO.
THANKS TO YOU,
I THINK I CAN DO THIS.
[HUFFS]
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE I CAME HERE
WANTING TO GIVE YOU A PEP TALK.
[WIND BLOWING]
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT'S COMING.
[GRUNTS]
SHOW YOURSELF!
[GASPS]
♪ [WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE]
[MIWA]
IT'S OKUMURA.
HE JUST CAME AFTER ME.
[SUGURO] IF YOU EVER HURT
ANY OF MY FRIENDS,
I SWORE I'D KILL YOU.
[YUKIO] CONTROL YOURSELF.
IF YOU GO ON ANOTHER RAMPAGE,
THEY'RE GO--
[SUGURO]
KONEKOMARU!