[CICADAS BUZZING]
[BELLS TOLLING]
[YAWNS]
LOOKS LIKE I SURVIVED
THE FIRST SEMESTER.
[MIWA]
HI, OKUMURA.
HEY, KONEKOMARU.
[MIWA]
I GUESS ALL THE ACADEMY'S
REGULAR STUDENTS...
ARE HEADING HOME
FOR THE SUMMER BREAK.
YOU GUYS ARE ALL
FROM KYOTO, RIGHT?
MAN, THAT PLACE
SOUNDS SO COOL.
[SUGURO]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, COOL?
IT'S JUST LIKE ANY OTHER TOWN.
HECK, WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF WE GET TO GO HOME YET.
UH--
YOU'RE SUPER BUSY,
BUT IF YOU GET THE TIME,
YOU SHOULD COME HOME.
IF I FEEL LIKE IT, YEAH.
YOU'RE HEADING HOME
FOR THE BREAK TOO, HUH?
MAN, IT'S GONNA
BE LONELY HERE.
SEE YOU GUYS
NEXT SEMESTER.
HAVE A GOOD BREAK.
IF YOU EVER GET THE URGE
TO HEAR MY VOICE AGAIN,
YOU CAN CALL ME DAY OR NIGHT.
YOU'RE SUCH A MORON!
[GIGGLES]
YOU'RE FUNNY.
[YUKIO]
I'M SURE YOU'RE ALL EXCITED
ABOUT SUMMER VACATION.
[BELL DINGING]
WE
LL, YOU'LL HAVE
TO HOLD THAT THOUGHT,
BECAUSE FOR
THE NEXT THREE DAYS,
YOU LUCKY EXWIRES...
WILL PARTICIPATE IN
A FIELD DRILL AT THE ACADEMY'S
TRAINING CAMP IN THE FOREST.
OF COURSE,
I'LL BE COMING ALONG...
AND SO WILL
MISS KIRIGAKURE.
MEOW-HOO.
NOW THE PURPOSE
OF THIS DRILL...
IS TO DETERMINE
WHETHER OR NOT YOU'RE READY
TO GO OUT ON MISSIONS,
SO STAY SHARP.
[ALL AGREEING]
♪ [MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[BELL DINGING]
[CICADAS BUZZING]
YEAH!
THIS IS GONNA BE RAD!
LIKE GOING ON A PICNIC!
I CAN SEE US NOW HANGING OUT
AROUND THE CAMPFIRE AT NIGHT
AND LEARNING FOLK DANCES.
[CHUCKLES, SIGHS]
[SCREAMING]
NO, NO, NO!
HEY, GET OFF ME!
IS HE GONNA BE OKAY?
UH, SHIMA'S ALWAYS HAD
A HARD TIME AROUND BUGS.
[BUZZING]
[SHIMA]
UH, IT'S SO HOT.
[MIWA] MY PACK'S HEAVY.
[YUKIO]
DURING THE DAY,
THE FOREST IS PEACEFUL.
BUT AT NIGHT IT BECOMES A HOTBED
OF LOWER-LEVEL DEMON ACTIVITY.
WE HAVE TO SET UP BASE CAMP
BEFORE THE SUN GOES DOWN.
[YUKIO]
PICK UP THE PACE.
LOOK AT THAT GUY.
ISN'T HE HOT IN THAT COAT?
[SHURA] YOU HEARD HIM.
GET A MOVE ON.
HUH?
UM, MA'AM,
WHERE'S YOUR BACKPACK?
IT'S OVER THERE.
HUH?
IT'S SO COLD.
IS IT SAFE TO DRINK?
[RIN LAUGHING]
I GET THE FEELING OKUMURA'S
ENERGY IS SUPERNATURAL.
[ALL PANTING]
[YUKIO]
THIS WILL BE OUR BASE CAMP.
THE BOYS AND I ARE GOING
TO START SETTING UP THE TENTS
AND BUILDING A FIRE.
WHILE THAT'S HAPPENING,
MISS KIRIGAKURE AND THE GIRLS...
ARE GOING TO DRAW A MAGIC CIRCLE
AROUND THE PERIMETER
AND GET DINNER STARTED.
RIGHT. LET'S GET MOVING.
HE FINALLY TOOK HIS COAT OFF.
UH-OH. SOMEONE'S
COME TO PARTY.
[CICADAS BUZZING]
THIS IS STARTING TO FEEL
MORE AND MORE
LIKE A PICNIC.
THIS IS CAMPING,
NOT A PICNIC.
AND WOULD YOU STOP HITTING
THE TENT LIKE THAT
OR IT'S GONNA--
[BOTH GASPING]
SEE? WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
[LAUGHS]
THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
YOU THINK SO?
THEY LOOK SUPER ANNOYING TO ME.
[SHIEMI] BOYS ARE KINDA
MYSTERIOUS, DON'T YOU THINK?
IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU'RE THE MYSTERIOUS ONE.
HUH?
LISTEN, I REALLY DON'T LIKE YOU.
UH, UM,
PLEASE SHOW ME HOW TO WEAR
THIS UNIFORM THE RIGHT WAY.
WHAT'S UP WITH HER?
SHE STILL TALKS TO ME EVEN AFTER
I SAID I DIDN'T LIKE HER.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
HMPH.
NOTHING, ALL RIGHT?
HURRY UP AND FINISH
YOUR SIDE OF THE CIRCLE.
YEAH, SURE.
HONESTLY, I'M SURROUNDED
BY FREAKS.
- YOU DONE DRAWING YET?
- [THINKING]
LIKE I SAID.
WE'RE ALMOST FINISHED.
[CRACKLING]
[BLOWING]
[KAMIKI]
OW!
HUH?
[RIN]
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
GIVE ME THAT!
[ALL GASPING]
[ALL]
THANKS FOR THE MEAL!
WHOA! MAN, THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
IF YOU EVER WANTED
TO SWITCH SIDES,
YOU'D MAKE SOMEONE
AN AWESOME WIFE.
YOU ARE REALLY
AN AMAZING COOK, OKUMURA.
SO YUMMY, RIN.
OH, THANKS, GUYS.
[LAUGHS]
COOKING IS THE ONLY VALUABLE
SKILL MY POOR BROTHER HAS.
SHUT IT,
YOU FOUR-EYED MOLE FACE.
[MIWA]
IT'S SO GOOD, I COULD EAT
PLATE AFTER PLATE.
[SHIMA]
YOU EAT WAY MORE
THAN I THOUGHT, MORIYAMA.
[THINKING]
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE FELT LIKE THIS.
[FUJIMOTO]
INSTEAD OF USING YOUR POWER
TO HURT OTHERS,
YOU SHOULD BE USING IT
TO HELP THEM.
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, RIN?
RIN!
[BIRD SINGING]
[THINKING]
OH, RIGHT.
I KNOW WHY.
I WAS ALWAYS DITCHING SCHOOL,
SO I NEVER REALLY GOT TO DO
STUFF LIKE THIS BEFORE.
HEY, OKUMURA.
WE GOT SOME DRINKS HERE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
[THINKING]
I GUESS THIS IS WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO HAVE FRIENDS.
IT'S COOL.
I'LL PICK ONE OUT MYSELF.
[GIGGLES]
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
WELL, I WAS A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT RIN, ESPECIALLY SINCE HE'S
BEEN ACTING SO STRANGE LATELY.
BUT HE'S HAVING FUN NOW.
THAT'S GOOD.
YOU REALLY DO CARE ABOUT HIM,
DON'T YOU?
- HMM?
- [CHUCKLES]
OH, NOTHING.
NEVER MIND.
OKAY, LISTEN UP.
I'M GOING TO EXPLAIN THE DRILL.
[DRUNKENLY]
YEAH. IT'S A TEST OF COURAGE.
I DARE YA.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE DRINKING
ON THE JOB.
OKAY, HOLD ON A SEC.
DIDN'T SHE SAY SHE WAS 18?
THAT MAKES HER A MINOR.
WAIT, 18?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
THIS YEAR SHE'LL BE TURNING
TWENTY-S--
UH-OH. MY HAND SLIPPED.
CUT THE SHIT
AND GET TO WORK ALREADY.
LOOK! I MADE HIM MAD.
[LAUGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
RIGHT. HERE'S THE RUNDOWN.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE YOU
SPREAD OUT TO FIND
AND LIGHT SOME LANTERNS...
THAT ARE HIDDEN
SOMEWHERE IN THE FOREST.
THE LANTERNS ARE LOCATED
WITHIN A 500-METER RADIUS
OF CAMP.
WHOEVER CAN KEEP THEIR LANTERN
LIT AND RETURN IT TO BASE CAMP
IN THE NEXT THREE DAYS...
WILL BE ELIGIBLE
TO GO ON ACTUAL COMBAT MISSIONS.
[ALL]
HMM?
HOWEVER, THERE ARE ONLY
THREE LANTERNS OUT THERE.
THEREFORE THERE ARE ONLY THREE
SLOTS OPEN TO GO ON MISSIONS.
BUT THAT MEANS--
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE CONTENTS
OF YOUR SHOULDER BAGS.
YOU'LL FIND THREE DAYS' WORTH
OF FOOD, WATER
AND OTHER NECESSITIES.
YOU'LL ALSO FIND A COMPASS,
FLASHLIGHT, ONE DEMON-REPELLING
BOTTLE ROCKET AND ONE MATCH.
BY RELYING ON YOUR STRENGTHS
AND USING YOUR ABILITIES
TO THEIR FULLEST,
YOU'LL FIND THE PATH TO SUCCESS.
SO ALL WE DO IS FIND A LANTERN,
LIGHT IT AND BRING IT BACK.
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A DRILL?
[SHURA LAUGHING]
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND
THE SITUATION.
THIS ISN'T GONNA BE
ANYTHING LIKE THE EXWIRE EXAM.
COULD YOU NOT--
YOU'LL BLOW YOUR COVER
IN THAT BIG, DARK FOREST.
SO YOU BETTER NOT BE FLAMING UP
OUT THERE, KID.
[GASPS]
[SHURA]
I'M AN INSPECTOR
AND I'M ON DUTY.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
IF ANYONE FINDS OUT
YOU GOT SATANIC POWERS,
THAT'S IT FOR YOU.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GO TELL
THE BRASS EVERYTHING I KNOW.
ONCE I DO, THE ARCHKNIGHT
AND THE PALADIN
ARE GONNA COME KILL YA,
AND THOSE GUYS
ARE WAY SCARIER
THAN ANY DEMON.
SO THINK REAL HARD
BEFORE YOU GO
POPPING OFF, OKAY?
HUH?
YOU WERE ALL EXCITED
A MINUTE AGO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
COME ON, YOU'RE NOT
CHICKENING OUT, ARE YA?
HUH?
BON.
I WAS THINKING.
THIS DRILL IS ACTUALLY DESIGNED
TO MAKE US COMPETE.
BUT THEN IF WE START
DOING THAT--
WE ARE GONNA BE
AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
[CRACKLING]
[SUGURO]
THEY'RE NOT GIVING US A CHOICE.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S EVERY PERSON
FOR THEMSELVES.
WE CAN'T HELP EACH OTHER.
[KAMIKI]
HE'S RIGHT. THERE'S ALL OF US
AND ONLY THREE SLOTS.
I KINDA LIKE THOSE ODDS.
[SHIMA]
THEN IT'S SETTLED, GUYS.
NO HARD FEELINGS, OKAY?
[THINKING]
I CAN'T USE MY POWER.
[YUKIO]
TAKE YOUR POSITIONS.
READY?
[GUNSHOT]
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
WHOA! WHERE DID ALL THE MOTHS
COME FROM?
[YUKIO]
AS I MENTIONED EARLIER,
AT NIGHT THE FOREST IS OVERRUN
WITH LOWER-LEVEL DEMONS.
WITH YOUR CURRENT KNOWLEDGE
AND ABILITIES,
YOU HAVE A SLIM CHANCE
OF SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETING
THIS MISSION.
[THINKING]
BLOOD-SUCKING MOTHS.
THEY MUST BE
SOME KIND OF CHUCHI.
IF YOU THINK YOU'RE IN DANGER,
LIGHT THE DEMON-REPELLING
ROCKET.
MISS KIRIGAKURE OR I
WILL COME FIND YOU
AND GET YOU OUT.
UM, IS THERE A REASON
WHY WE'RE ONLY GETTING
ONE MATCH?
IF YOU USE IT TO LIGHT
THE ROCKET, YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO LIGHT THE LANTERN,
SO YOU SHOULD THINK
VERY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING IT.
[KAMIKI SCREAMING]
I HUMBLY APPEAL TO THEE,
OH, GODDESS INARI.
GRANT MY REQUEST.
LEAVE NOT MY PRAYERS TO THEE
UNFULFILLED.
- [GROWLING]
- WHEN DAVID SERVED GOD'S
PURPOSE IN HIS OWN GENERATION,
HE FELL ASLEEP AND WAS BURIED
WITH HIS ANCESTORS...
AND HIS BODY DECAYED.
[EXPLOSION]
YOU WILL NOT LET
YOUR HOLY ONE SEE DECAY.
[EXPLOSION]
HEY, NEE, I NEED
SOME BUG-REPELLENT ROUX.
- NEE!
- [GASPS]
NEE? NEE, NEE, NEE!
[GASPS]
NEE!
[SHIEMI SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
THAT'S SHIEMI.
SHIEMI, WHERE ARE YOU?
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
SHIEMI!
GET OUTTA HERE!
SHIEMI. SHIEMI.
[GASPS]
[EXPLOSION]
[RIN]
GET LOST!
UH-- OH, CRAP.
CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN,
CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN, CALM DOWN.
[WINGS FLUTTERING]
[PANTING]
I'M SO STUPID!
I DID IT AGAIN.
USING MY FLAMES
IS BECOMING A HABIT.
I HAVEN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
- [RUSTLING]
- [GASPS]
OKUMURA, WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
[GASPS]
YOU GONNA ANSWER ME
OR WHAT?
[THINKING]
DID HE SEE IT?
WHAT HAPPENED TO MORIYAMA?
SHE OKAY?
Y-Y-YEAH. I THINK SO.
SHE'S UNCONSCIOUS THOUGH.
HEY, TURN OFF
THAT LIGHT ALREADY.
HELLO? THE MOTHS
ARE ATTRACTED TO IT.
OH. RIGHT. SORRY.
I GUESS HE DIDN'T SEE IT.
YEAH, SO, ANYWAY, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT BLUE LIGHT WAS
JUST NOW?
[GASPS]
IT HAPPENED SO FAST
AND WAS SO BRIGHT,
I COULDN'T TELL
WHAT IT WAS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T GET
A GOOD LOOK EITHER.
MAYBE IT WAS
ONE OF THOSE, UM--
WHAT DO YOU CALL THOSE THINGS?
[LAUGHS]
I GUESS HE DIDN'T SEE ME
BURST INTO FLAMES AFTER ALL.
THANK GOD.
SO, UH,
WHAT YOU DOING OVER HERE?
WHAT AM I--
I CAME TO HELP HER, DORK.
YEAH, BUT YOU SAID
WE COULDN'T HELP
EACH OTHER.
SHUT UP!
AFTER HEARING THAT SCREAM,
WHO WOULDN'T COME RUNNING?
[LAUGHS]
EASY.
SHIEMI'S
GONNA BE FINE, OKAY?
EVERYTHING'S COOL.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF HER
FROM HERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN COOL?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH HER?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I'M GONNA TAKE HER
BACK TO CAMP...
AND THEN I'LL COME BACK.
[HUFFS]
COCKY LITTLE--
RIN?
SHIEMI.
OH, NEE!
N-NEE.
HEY, CALM DOWN.
DON'T WORRY.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE
YOUR MAGIC CIRCLE PAPERS,
YOU CAN SUMMON HIM
OVER AND OVER.
THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S WEIRD.
THEY SHOULD BE RIGHT HERE
IN MY BAG.
I WONDER IF THEY FELL OUT
WHEN I GOT ATTACKED.
WAS THAT REAL?
DID A GIANT MOTH ATTACK ME?
[FLUTTERING]
[RUSTLING]
GET DOWN!
- [GRUNTING]
- SHIMA!
HEY, BON.
WHAT'S EVERYONE DOING
OVER HERE?
HANGING OUT?
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AND TURN THAT OFF.
OH.
[CLICKS]
WELL, THIS HORDE OF MOTHS
COVERED ME UP,
AND AFTER THAT I SORT
OF DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
YEAH, TYPICAL SHIMA.
[CELL PHONES RINGING]
- MINE'S RINGING TOO.
- [BEEPS]
HMM.
IT'S KONEKOMARU.
HE SAYS
HE FOUND A LANTERN.
[BOTH GASP]
"I CAN'T DO THIS ALONE."
HE'S ASKING FOR HELP.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
NOT EVEN 10 MINUTES IN,
AND HE GOES
AND USES HIS POWER.
HELL, WHATEVER.
IT'S SO DARK OUT THERE, I BET
IT BLINDED ANYONE WHO SAW IT.
I'M STARTING TO SEE
HOW FUTILE IT IS
TO KEEP HIS POWERS SECRET.
[GUFFAWS]
YOU SOUND
LIKE AN OLD MAN.
ALL RIGHT, SHURA,
LET'S HAVE IT.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
WHY ARE YOU WASTING TIME HERE
WHEN YOU COULD JUST GO TELL
THE VATICAN?
[GULPING]
AH-HA!
I PUT MY REPORT ON HOLD
'CAUSE I DECIDED TO TEACH HIM
HOW TO USE HIS SWORD.
WHA-- YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT?
SERIOUSLY?
UH-HUH.
HE HAD THE BALLS TO TELL ME
HE WAS GONNA BE THE PALADIN.
[LAUGHS]
[GROANS]
HMM. I GUESS I'M A SUCKER
FOR A GUY WITH BIG AMBITIONS.
YEAH, BUT WHEN SHIRO ASKED ME,
I WAS ALL,
"NO WAY. ARE YOU CRAZY?"
- Y-Y-YOU MEAN DAD--
- I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT AS FAR AS
TRAINING RIN GOES, YOUR DAD WAS
RIGHT TO COME TO ME ABOUT IT.
THAT WOMAN DEFINITELY KNOWS
WE'RE HERE... WATCHING.
SHE'S SUCH A BRAT.
AMAIMON, HAVE YOU SAID
YOUR HELLOS TO THE MASTER
OF THE FOREST YET?
YES. MANY OF HIS BRETHREN
HAVE BEEN KILLED, SO HE'S
BEEN QUITE COOPERATIVE.
I THINK I SHOULD STICK AROUND
AND WATCH THE PROCEEDINGS
THIS TIME.
THAT HORRID WOMAN HAS HIDDEN
THE KURIKARA SWORD.
I WONDER IF THERE'S SOMETHING
I CAN DO TO MAKE THE BOY SNAP.
HEY, WHILE IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU MOTIVATED,
I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU DO AS I SAY THIS TIME.
HE HASN'T HEARD
A WORD I'VE SAID.
[ALL GASPING]
WHOA. UH, YEAH.
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU COULD LUG THIS BACK
ALL BY YOURSELF.
THIS THING'S A LANTERN?
IT'S HUGE.
IS THAT A STONE LANTERN?
[SUGURO]
IT'S A PEG LANTERN.
[BOTH GASP]
IT WAITS IN THE NIGHT
FOR SOMEONE TO COME LIGHT IT.
ONCE IT'S LIT,
IT STARTS MOVING AROUND.
IT EATS LIVING THINGS
FOR FUEL.
IT ESPECIALLY
LIKES GIRLS.
[GASPS]
IT'S A DEMON THAT'LL ONLY STOP
WHEN IT RUNS OUT OF FUEL
OR WHEN THE SUN COMES UP.
ONCE I SAW IT, I REALIZED
WE MUST HAVE MISUNDERSTOOD
THE REAL PURPOSE OF THIS DRILL.
YEAH. FOR THIS DRILL,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO HELP EACH OTHER AFTER ALL.
[SHIMA]
WAIT A SECOND, BON.
YOU SPECIFICALLY SAID
THAT WE CAN'T HELP
EACH OTHER OUT.
I-- LOOK, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT HE MEANT...
WHEN HE SAID THERE WERE ONLY
THREE SLOTS AVAILABLE.
[MIWA] HE'S GOT A POINT.
MR. OKUMURA NEVER ACTUALLY SAID
THREE PEOPLE.
WHATEVER.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
DOES ANYBODY KNOW KAMIKI
AND TAKARA'S PHONE NUMBERS?
[ALL]
HMM-MM.
I TRY TO GET IZUMO'S
ALL THE TIME, BUT SHE KEEPS
TURNING ME DOWN.
- [SUGURO GROANS]
- UM, I, UH, SORT OF CAME UP
WITH A FORMATION...
WHERE THE FIVE OF US
CAN CARRY IT OUT.
OKAY, THIS IS HOW
WE'RE GONNA SEAL IT...
TO KEEP IT FROM MOVING AROUND
ONCE IT'S LIT.
THEN BON WILL RECITE
THE CORRESPONDING
SCRIPTURE...
SINCE HE'S ALREADY
GOT IT MEMORIZED.
[FLUTTERING]
BEFORE WE LIGHT THE PEG LANTERN,
WE'LL NEED TO GATHER UP
LOTS OF CHUCHI TO FEED IT.
AND WE'LL NEED A CONSTANT SUPPLY
TO KEEP THE LIGHT
FROM GOING OUT.
THAT'S MORIYAMA'S JOB.
WHOA! INCOMING!
[FLUTTERING]
[MIWA]
ONCE THE CHUCHI SHOW UP,
SHIMA AND I WILL BE THE ONES
GUARDING MORIYAMA
FROM THEIR ATTACKS.
FINALLY,
THE PERSON WITH
THE MOST HORSEPOWER WILL BE
THE ONE WHO PULLS THE CART.
[SHIEMI]
WOW, RIN, YOU'RE STRONG.
[SHIMA]
OKUMURA, WHAT PLANET
DO YOU COME FROM?
YOU GUYS, LET'S GO,
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
[WHISTLING]
WHAT'S THAT?
SOMEONE GAVE UP ALREADY?
WELL, THAT WAS FAST.
YOU HANDLE THIS ONE.
[GROANS]
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
BUT DON'T FALL ASLEEP.
I MEAN IT.
[GRUNTING]
WHO'S THAT?
IT'S EITHER KAMIKI OR TAKARA.
[GASPS, GRUNTS]
[SUGURO CHANTING]
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY DID WE STOP?
[RIN]
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
ABOUT THIS?
- [CHANTING CONTINUES]
- [BOTH GROAN]
[SHIMA SHOUTS]
OH, HOLY HELL, LOOK DOWN!
THERE'S TONS OF 'EM!
OH, MY GOD.
I THINK
I'M GONNA PISS MYSELF.
MAYBE YOU'D FEEL BETTER
IF YOU DID.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
[MIWA] OKUMURA,
PLEASE DON'T SAY THINGS
LIKE THAT TO HIM.
ONCE SOMEONE
PEES THEIR PANTS,
THAT'S IT. GAME OVER.
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
BON?
[SHOUTS]
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
"KAHN." THAT'S SANSKRIT.
LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING ELSE
IS BEING SEALED HERE.
HEY, GUYS! BE CAREFUL!
[CONTINUES CHANTING]
ALL RIGHT, HOW?
OH, OKAY.
I THINK I SEE
WHERE THIS IS GOING.
HUH?
- [CHANTING CONTINUES]
- OH.
[RIN] KONEKOMARU AND I
ARE GONNA TAKE THE CART
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
THE BUG SWAMP'S SHALLOW,
SO... I'M GONNA
WALK THROUGH IT?
[MIWA]
ONCE WE'RE THERE, I'M GONNA
STAND BY WITH A TALISMAN.
MEANWHILE, OVER ON THIS SIDE,
SHIMA WILL WAIT WITH MORIYAMA
ON HIS SHOULDERS.
[SHIMA] THEN BON'S GONNA
REMOVE THE TALISMAN
AND UNSEAL THE PEG LANTERN...
AND THEN I'LL CARRY MORIYAMA
ON MY SHOULDERS...
THROUGH THE BUG SWAMP
TO THE OTHER SIDE?
[MIWA] AFTER THAT, THE PEG
LANTERN IS GOING TO GO AFTER
ITS FAVORITE FOOD, MORIYAMA,
AND THAT'S WHEN
I'M GONNA SEAL IT AGAIN
BY APPLYING THE TALISMAN.
[CHANTING]
SUGURO, MAN, YOUR
DRAWINGS ARE EPIC!
[SHIMA LAUGHING]
YOU GUYS WANT ME TO GO WADING
THROUGH THAT BUG SWAMP...
WHILE MY HEAD'S GETTING SQUEEZED
BETWEEN MORIYAMA'S THIGHS?
I'LL DIE BEFORE WE MAKE IT.
[MIWA]
SHIMA, THIS ISN'T THE TIME
TO ENTERTAIN YOUR LIBIDO.
COME ON, KONEKO, DON'T BE MEAN.
[RIN]
FINE. WHATEVER.
I'LL CARRY HER OVER.
UH, HANG ON,
'CAUSE WE'RE DOING THIS.
UH, OKAY.
[SHRIEKS]
[BOTH SHOUTING]
[SHIEMI]
IT'S SO HIGH!
HEY, EASY ON THE HAIR.
OH, SORRY.
[BLUBBERING]
THEY'RE POPPING.
WE'RE GOOD TO GO OVER HERE.
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
WE'RE SET HERE TOO.
ALL RIGHT, GIDDYAP.
[GROWLING]
[LANTERN ROARS]
HERE IT COMES.
[GRUNTS]
- [GROWLING]
- OVER HERE!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TEASE IT.
[ROARS]
[SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS]
KAHN!
[CHANTING]
WE DID IT!
- RIN, WE DID IT!
- [PANTING]
[LAUGHS]
HEY, OKUMURA, GRAB ON.
I'LL PULL YOU UP.
IT'S COOL.
I'M GOOD.
[MIWA CHANTING]
[SIGHS]
WELL, NOW THAT
THAT'S OVER WITH--
[CREAKING]
UH--
OH.
[GROANING]
- [GASPS]
- RIN! BEHIND YOU!
HUH?
[SHOUTING]
♪ [WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE]
[AMAIMON LAUGHING]
[YUKIO]
RIN, IT'S A TRAP!
DON'T FALL FOR IT!
[RIN]
I-I GUESS I JUST DON'T
GOT IT IN ME...
TO KEEP LYING TO EVERYONE,
SO I DECIDED.