[ SQUEAKING ]
[ RIN ]
I SUPPOSE I'VE KNOWN EVER
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE KID...
THAT I'M JUST NOT NORMAL.
[ WOMAN #1 ]
HOW COULD A CHILD
BE SO FEROCIOUS?
[ WOMAN #2 ]
I WISH HE'D JUST
DISAPPEAR FROM HERE.
[ WOMAN #3 ]
YOU'D THINK
HE WAS A DEMON'S CHILD.
BUT I'M NOT.
I'M NOT A DEMON.
NO, I'M NOT!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SQUEAKING ]
THE ROAD IS UNMARKED
FOR THOSE WITHOUT FAITH.
THE HAND OF GOD WILL FLING THEM
FROM JACOB'S LADDER.
[ SCREECHING ]
COME ON!
SERIOUSLY?
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLING ]
STRAY DOGS?
[ GAGS ]
THEY STINK!
THEY'RE ALL GHOULS,
DEMONS WHO POSSESS
THE LONG DEAD.
- GHOULS?
- LUCKY FOR YOU.
IF THIS WEREN'T JAPAN,
WE'D BE BESET BY GHOULS
IN HUMAN FORM.
THERE'S NOTHING LUCKY
ABOUT THIS.
WAIT. YOU'RE GONNA USE
A BOMB?
NOT TO WORRY.
IT'S JUST HOLY WATER.
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S NOT EXACTLY
A WALK IN THE PARK
TO BABY-SIT AT MY AGE, YOU KNOW.
- WHO YOU CALLING A BABY?
- NOW LET'S GET HOME
WHILE WE CAN.
- ARE YOU SAYING IT'S NOT OVER?
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU--
DEMONS OF ALL SPECIES
WILL BE COMING AFTER YOU.
THE SUN WILL BE DOWN SOON.
THAT'S WHEN THE DEMONS
REALLY BECOME ACTIVE.
♪ [ MAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING AT ALL?
MMM.
NOT EVEN THAT YOU TRIED
TO WASTE OKUMURA?
OR THAT HIS BODY
SUDDENLY BURST INTO FLAMES?
I'M SURE.
I DON'T REMEMBER
A SINGLE DAMN THING.
[ ALL GROAN ]
LAST NIGHT, I-I-I SPOTTED YOU
500 YEN FOR DINNER, REMEMBER?
YEAH! AND-AND-AND I PAID
FOR ALL YOUR HOSPITAL BILLS,
MAN.
HEY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
I PAID FOR THAT
MAGICAL POEMY PILLOW...
YOU SAID YOU'D BEEN WANTING
SO BAD.
THAT SO?
I'M SORRY I CAUSED YOU
ANY INCON--
- WAIT.
ARE YOU MESSING WITH ME?
- [ BLOWS LANDING ]
BUT I REALLY DID PAY
THOSE BILLS.
HUH? FOR WHAT?
WE ALREADY TOLD YOU, MAN.
YOU GOT INTO A FIGHT
WITH RIN OKUMURA.
I FOUGHT WITH OKUMURA?
YEAH, YOU WERE GONNA WASTE HIM,
BUT HE WASTED YOU INSTEAD.
HE SENT YOU
TO THE HOSPITAL, MAN.
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
I AM PRETTY MUCH ACHING
ALL OVER.
HMM.
UH-OH. HE'S TALKING
TO HIMSELF.
YOU THINK MAYBE HE HIT
HIS HEAD TOO HARD?
HE MUST HAVE.
THAT BASTARD OKUMURA IS MESSING
WITH ME AGAIN, DAMN HIM.
OKUMURA, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'RE A DEMON OR A MAD DOG,
BUT YOU'RE OKUMURA, YOU BASTARD!
OKUMURA. OKUMURA. OKUMURA!
OKUMURA! OKUMURA!
DON'T GIVE ME THAT CRAP,
OKUMURA.
HE'S FLIPPING OUT.
I CAN'T HANDLE THIS
ANYMORE.
[ SHOUTING ]
I'M GETTING THE HELL
OUTTA HERE!
WAIT FOR ME!
[ LAUGHS ]
YES, JUST AS I THOUGHT.
THIS BODY IS AN EXCELLENT FIT.
NOW, OUR YOUNG PRINCE,
WHERE, OH, WHERE CAN YOU BE?
[ RUNNING FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
[ GRUNTING ]
WELCOME HOME.
HOW DID IT GO?
I PURGED ALL OF THE COAL TARS,
AND I TRIPLE REINFORCED
THE SPIRITUAL BARRIER
ALL AROUND THE MONASTERY.
DOUBLE IT AGAIN.
IT SURELY WON'T HOLD
UNTIL MORNING.
WE ARE BEING ATTACKED
BY A KINSMAN OF ASTAROTH.
I WANT THE SEWERS DOUSED
WITH TRIPLE-C DENSITY
HOLY WATER.
NOT A SINGLE ONE
MUST BE ALLOWED TO INFILTRATE.
YES, FATHER.
[ CRASHING ]
[ ROARING ]
[ SHRIEKING ]
[ CONTINUOUS CRASHING ]
[ CREATURES SHRIEKING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
COME WITH ME.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
THE KOMA SWORD.
ALSO KNOWN AS KURIKARA,
AN ANCIENT AND LEGENDARY
DEMON-SLAYING SWORD.
MANY YEARS AGO, I TRANSFERRED
YOUR DEMONIC POWERS
TO THIS SWORD...
AND SEALED THE SCABBARD.
WAIT. MY... POWERS?
THIS SWORD IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN YOUR LIFE.
IT MUST NEVER FALL
INTO ANYONE'S HANDS.
KEEP IT BY YOUR SIDE,
EVEN WHEN YOU SLEEP.
REMEMBER,
THIS MUST NEVER BE DRAWN.
ONCE DRAWN, YOUR DEMONIC POWERS
WILL BE AWAKENED,
AND YOU CAN NEVER GO BACK
TO BEING HUMAN.
HOLD ON. IF I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
SOME KIND OF DEMON,
THEN WHAT ABOUT YUKIO?
- DON'T TELL ME HE'S ONE.
- EVEN THOUGH YOU AND YUKIO
ARE FRATERNAL TWINS,
YUKIO WAS UNDERDEVELOPED
AND FRAIL AND PROVED TOO WEAK
TO SUSTAIN THE POWER.
YOU ALONE
INHERITED THESE POWERS.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ROARING, LAUGHING ]
DID EVERYBODY KNOW
ABOUT THIS?
THAT I'M NOT REALLY
A HUMAN BEING?
THAT I'M THE SPAWN OF THE DEVIL?
[ GHOULS SQUEAKING ]
THIS IS IT, THE PLACE
WHERE OUR YOUNG PRINCE DWELLS
IN HIS TRANSIENT HUMAN FORM...
HIDDEN FROM THE WORLD.
[ CAR APPROACHES, HORN HONKS ]
YOU IDIOT!
WHAT IN THE HELL
WERE YOU THINKING?
HEY.
- [ GROWLS ]
- [ BLOW LANDS ]
THAT HURT, DAMN IT!
DON'T WORRY, MY YOUNG PRINCE.
I'M ON MY WAY.
- [ LAUGHS ]
- WHY THE HELL
DID YOU KEEP QUIET...
ABOUT SOMETHING SO IMPORTANT
ALL THIS TIME?
I'LL RAISE YOU
AS LONG AS YOU REMAIN HUMAN.
YOU SEE,
IN ORDER TO KEEP YOU ALIVE,
YOU OF DEMONIC ORIGIN,
IT WAS THE ONE CONDITION
THAT HAD TO BE MET.
CONDITION?
I NEEDED TO RAISE YOU
AS A HUMAN BEING.
THAT'S WHY
I CHOSE TO SAY NOTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL ABOUT THE SECRET
OF YOU AND YOUR BROTHER'S BIRTH.
- [ LOUD CRASH ]
- [ GASPS ]
COME ON!
[ GASPS ]
[ ROARING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
[ ASTAROTH ]
I HAVE COME FOR YOU,
MY YOUNG PRINCE.
LET US RETURN HOME TO GEHENNA.
- [ ROARS ]
- [ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
COME MORNING,
THE DEMONIC ACTIVITY
WILL TAPER OFF.
YOU'VE GOT TO LEAVE RIGHT NOW
AND HIDE YOURSELF
WHERE THE DEMONS WON'T FIND YOU.
HIDE?
WHERE, FOR PETE'S SAKE?
HERE'S MY CELL PHONE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE NUMBER
SAVED IN IT.
HE'S A GOOD FRIEND.
CALL HIM AS SOON AS YOU LEAVE
THE MONASTERY.
I'M CERTAIN HE'LL BE WILLING
TO TAKE YOU IN AND PROTECT YOU.
HEY!
[ SHOUTS ]
BUT WE'RE NOT DONE TALKING YET!
THE ROAD IS NOT MARKED
FOR THOSE WHO ARE LACKING FAITH.
BILLOWING FOG BLOCKS
THE GATES OF HEAVEN.
PROTECT RIN!
BEGONE, DEMONS.
IN MY FIST IS GOD.
- [ SNARLING ]
- AND IN MY SOUL, THE DEVIL!
SHOW YOURSELF,
GUARDIAN SPIRIT MALKIN.
[ SCREECHING ]
- [ SCREECHING ]
- [ ROARING ]
DAMN THOSE EXORCISTS!
[ SHOUTING ]
LET ME OUT, OLD MAN!
LET ME OUT!
ME? A DEMON?
DAMN IT!
[ WOMAN ]
HOW FEROCIOUS!
HE'S A DEMON'S CHILD.
[ YOUNG RIN ]
BUT I'M NOT A DEMON!
[ RIN, THINKING ]
I'M NOT. I'M NOT.
[ LINE RINGING ]
- [ BEEPS ]
- [ WIND RISING ]
RIN.
[ SHOTGUN COCKING ]
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO HIT?
MALKIN, NO!
- [ GRUNTING ]
- HE'S FAST.
[ SHOUTS, GROANS ]
KYODO!
THE LORD GIVETH,
AND THE LORD TAKETH AWAY.
LIFE AND JOYOUSNESS,
PRAISED BE THE LORD!
[ GROANING ]
[ ASTAROTH LAUGHING ]
NOW ROT AND WITHER AWAY!
[ GROWLS ]
HOW DARE YOU, HUMAN!
MARUTA!
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOU NOW.
[ ROARING ]
HE'S ENORMOUS.
I'M GOING TO RIP THE GUTS...
OUT OF EACH AND EVERY LAST ONE
OF YOU BEFORE I'M THROUGH.
LIKE I SAID, WE'RE NOT DONE
TALKING YET, YOU OLD FART.
YOUNG PRINCE, WHAT ON EARTH--
LORD IN HEAVEN,
HANG A MILLSTONE
AROUND HIS NECK...
SO THAT HE MAY NEVER AGAIN RISE
FROM THE DEPTHS
INHABITED BY LEVIATHAN.
[ WHIMPERS ]
STOP!
UNABLE TO SEE
AND UNABLE TO HEAR,
IMPRISONED BY ETERNAL DARKNESS!
[ ROARING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ FUJIMOTO ]
NAGATOMO, BRING THE CAR AROUND.
- RIGHT.
- IZUMI AND KYODO,
I WANT YOU TO BRAND
THIS YOUNGSTER
WITH THE MARK OF TETRAMORPH.
AND MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T FORGET
TO PURIFY HIM.
[ BOTH ]
YES, FATHER.
WAIT A SEC.
SHOULDN'T YOU TAKE CARE
OF YOUR OWN WOUNDS FIRST?
NO. RIGHT NOW OUR FIRST
AND ONLY PRIORITY IS TO GET YOU
SAFELY INTO HIDING.
DON'T EVER FORGET THAT IT'S YOU
THE DEMONS ARE COMING AFTER,
RIN.
IS THAT RIGHT?
SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS THAT EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE
AS LONG AS I'M HISTORY.
NO, RIN.
FINE. I'LL BE HAPPY
TO BOUNCE.
- YOU'D FEEL A LOT BETTER
IF I DID ANYWAY.
- RIN!
LET GO! YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WANTS TO KICK ME
OUT OF HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME
THAT I'M THE SCREWED-UP SON.
ACTUALLY, WE'RE NOT
EVEN RELATED, SO I'M
THE SCREWED-UP STRANGER, RIGHT?
- STOP IT!
- COME ON,
WHY DON'T YOU ADMIT IT?
YOU'RE JUST SICK AND TIRED
OF PRETENDING TO BE MY FAMILY.
OR IS IT AGAINST YOUR RELIGION
TO SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
OR WAIT, IS IT BECAUSE
YOU WANT ONE LAST TIME
TO PLAY THE PERFECT DAD?
GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU'RE NOT MY FATHER.
YOU'RE NOBODY TO ME.
DON'T EVER LET ME SEE YOU ACTING
LIKE MY FATHER AGAIN!
[ ALL GASPING ]
IT WILL BE MORNING SOON.
HURRY.
GO GET YOUR THINGS.
YEAH, OKAY.
[ GROANS ]
NO, IT CAN'T BE.
FATHER FUJIMOTO!
STAY AWAY.
DON'T COME ANOTHER STEP
CLOSER TO ME.
[ SHATTERING ]
WH-WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ EVIL CHUCKLING ]
AT LONG LAST,
I'VE CLAIMED THIS BODY
AS MY OWN.
- OLD MAN?
- HMM?
WELL, FINALLY, WE MEET AT LAST,
MY LONG LOST SON.
JUST KIDDING!
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT THE HELL'S WRONG
WITH YOU, OLD MAN?
HE'S BEEN POSSESSED.
SATAN HAS ENTERED HIM
AND TAKEN OVER HIS BODY.
HUH?
EXACTLY AS HE SAYS.
I AM SATAN.
I AM THE RULER OF GEHENNA...
AND YOUR TRUE FATHER.
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME PAPA
IF YOU WANT.
[ LAUGHS ]
FATHER FUJIMOTO!
- SHUT UP!
- [ SHOUTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
- NO, STOP IT!
- DON'T YOU DARE SPOIL
OUR TOUCHING REUNION.
I'M AFRAID TIME
IS RUNNING OUT FOR ME.
[ BONES SNAPPING ]
YOU SEE, MY POWER
IS TOO OVERWHELMING
FOR ASSIAH,
AND SO WHATEVER I POSSESS
IS DOOMED NOT TO LAST LONG.
JUST LIKE THIS MAN'S BODY,
AND JUST LIKE YOUR MOTHER,
MY SON.
[ GASPING ]
[ SHRIEKING ]
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
GEHENNA GATE,
THE MAGICAL DOOR
LINKING ASSIAH AND GEHENNA.
NOW, LET'S BE OFF.
NO. STAY AWAY.
STAY AWAY!
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
DID YOU JUST PISS YOUR PANTS
OR SOMETHING?
PATHETIC.
JUST GET YOUR DEMONIC POWERS
BACK ALREADY.
[ SHOUTS ]
I'M NOT A DEMON!
I'M A HUMAN!
WHAT? IS THAT ME?
THEN I REALLY AM--
THE DARK BLOOD
OF THE GOD OF GEHENNA
RUNS THICK IN YOUR VEINS,
YET YOUR BODY EXISTS
HERE IN ASSIAH.
YOU'RE AN EXTRAORDINARY BEING,
YOU KNOW.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
SPLENDID BIRTH CRIES!
TODAY IS THE DAY OF YOUR REBIRTH
AS A DEMON, MY SON.
SOMEBODY!
HELP ME!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MY BELOVED SON!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ FUJIMOTO ]
NO. IT'S NOT TRUE.
- [ GRUNTS ]
- [ GASPS ]
[ FUJIMOTO ]
THAT BOY--
THAT BOY IS MY SON,
AND I'M TAKING HIM BACK.
CURSES. WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
DAMN YOU, EXORCIST!
[ GASPS ]
[ THUD ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
SO YOU MEAN TO SACRIFICE
YOUR OWN LIFE FOR HIM?
YOU ASTOUND ME,
YOU WRETCHED PRIEST.
HOWEVER,
IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE.
GEHENNA GATE HAS TAKEN
A HOLD OF YOU,
AND IT WILL NEVER LET YOU GO.
OLD MAN!
HANG ON!
HANG ON, OLD MAN!
DON'T GIVE UP!
DAMN!
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ YOUNG RIN ]
HEY, DAD?
[ YOUNGER FUJIMOTO ] YES?
WHY DO YOU THINK I'M DIFFERENT
FROM EVERYONE ELSE?
DO YOU THINK THAT MAYBE
I'M A DEMON'S CHILD?
NOT AT ALL.
- OH.
- YOU'RE A NORMAL
HUMAN CHILD, RIN.
[ RIN ]
OKAY.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S THE KOMA SWORD.
[ GRUNTS ]
STOP IT, RIN! DID YOU FORGET
WHAT FATHER FUJIMOTO
TOLD YOU ALREADY?
IF YOU DRAW THAT SWORD,
YOU WILL--
[ GRUNTING ]
OLD MAN.
IF IT STINGS YOU SO MUCH,
THEN GIVE ME A GLIMPSE
OF HOW MUCH YOU'VE MATURED.
[ RIN, THINKING ]
LISTEN TO ME. I HAVEN'T
EVEN SHOWN YOU ANYTHING YET.
DON'T DIE, OLD MAN!
[ SNARLING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, DAD.
[ YUKIO ]
RIN?
♪ [ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ RAIN PATTERING ]
[ MURMURING ]
[ FUJIMOTO ]
WELCOME HOME, RIN.
DID YOU FIND YOURSELF A JOB?
REALLY? I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT A HULKING LOUT
YOU'VE BECOME.
HERE'S MY CELL PHONE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE NUMBER
SAVED IN IT.
HE'S A GOOD FRIEND.
CALL HIM AS SOON AS YOU LEAVE
THE MONASTERY.
I'M CERTAIN HE'LL BE WILLING
TO TAKE YOU IN AND PROTECT YOU.
[ PHONE BEEPS ]
[ LINE RINGING ]
- ♪ [ CELL PHONE TUNE ]
- [ GASPS ]
AT LAST WE MEET.
I AM MEPHISTO PHELES,
PRECEPT OF THE JAPAN BRANCH
OF THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
FATHER FUJIMOTO
WAS A DEAR FRIEND.
MY THOUGHTS ARE WITH YOU
IN YOUR TIME OF SORROW.
ARE YOU ALL EXORCISTS TOO?
I'M AFRAID WE ARE, YES.
AND WE KNOW ALL ABOUT YOU.
FATHER FUJIMOTO
TRIED TO RAISE YOU
AS A NORMAL HUMAN CHILD.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOUR TRUE NATURE
DECIDED TO POKE
ITS UGLY LITTLE HEAD OUT.
NOT TO OFFEND,
BUT HAVING THE SON OF SATAN
RUNNING LOOSE IN ASSIAH...
PUTS THE WHOLE OF MANKIND
IN THE WORST JEOPARDY.
THEREFORE, WE ARE HERE
IN THE NAME OF THE VATICAN...
TO EXTERMINATE YOU
BEFORE YOU POP OFF AGAIN.
HEY, I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA
OFFER ME PROTECTION.
OH, THAT'S PERSONAL, DEAR BOY.
THIS IS BUSINESS.
NOW THEN, YOU HAVE
TWO OPTIONS TO CHOOSE FROM.
THE FIRST ONE IS
WE KILL YOU.
THE SECOND--
TRY TO KILL US AND RUN.
APOLOGIES.
YOU ALSO HAVE THE OPTION
OF COMMITTING SUICIDE.
THERE, THAT'S THREE.
NOW THEN,
YOU HAVE YOUR OPTIONS.
MAKE YOUR CHOICE, SIR.
- LET ME JOIN UP WITH YOU.
- HUH?
YOU CAN SAY WHAT YOU WANT,
THINK WHAT YOU WANT.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN.
BUT GET THIS STRAIGHT--
SATAN IS NOT MY FATHER.
I ONLY HAVE ONE DAD,
AND HIS NAME WAS SHIRO FUJIMOTO.
HANG ON, KID.
YOU WANT TO BE AN EXORCIST
LIKE FATHER FUJIMOTO?
UH, MAY I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHY WOULD SOMEONE LIKE YOU
WANT TO BECOME AN EXORCIST?
I'M GONNA BEAT THE SHIT
OUT OF SATAN!
[ GULPS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT THE HELL
IS SO FUNNY?
YOU'RE KIDDING!
THE SON OF SATAN WORKING
AS AN EXORCIST?
[ LAUGHS ]
HOW BRILLIANT!
I HAVEN'T LAUGHED
SO HARD IN AGES.
THAT IS JUST CLASSIC!
I'M SERIOUS ABOUT THIS.
I DON'T DOUBT IT.
YOU'RE ON, SIR.
- WAIT! SIR PHELES!
- HUH? IT'S OKAY?
I CAN DEFINITELY
PULL SOME STRINGS.
BUT I MUST WARN YOU--
YOU'VE CHOSEN
A THORNY PATH TO FOLLOW.
YOU JUST MIGHT END UP REGRETTING
YOUR DECISION NOT TO DIE TODAY.
YOUR FATE WILL ALMOST CERTAINLY
BE QUITE TERRIBLE AND AGONIZING.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN. I'M NOT
A HUMAN OR A DEMON ANYMORE.
MY ONLY CHOICE NOW
IS TO MOVE ON.
I'M GONNA BECOME AN EXORCIST.
WELCOME TO TRUE CROSS
ACADEMY.
STARTING TODAY,
YOU ARE A FULL-TIME STUDENT
AT OUR PRESTIGIOUS INSTITUTION.
[ RIN ]
JUST DROP THE ACT!
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
[ YUKIO ]
OR BETTER YET, DIE.