[ RIN ] FOR 15 YEARS,
THIS PLACE WAS HOME
TO YUKIO AND ME.
[ FUJIMOTO ]
DINNER TIME, BOYS.
HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
YEAH!
YES! WHAT'D YOU MAKE?
NOTHING MUCH.
JUST MY AWESOME CURRY.
WOW!
WHY HASN'T YUKIO
ASKED ME ANYTHING...
ABOUT HOW THE OLD MAN DIED?
ABOUT ME?
I WONDER WHAT HE'S THINKING.
[ METAL SQUEAKING ]
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
YOU BOYS ARE LEAVING US.
WE'RE GONNA MISS
HAVING YOU AROUND.
HE'S RIGHT. YOU'RE ALWAYS
WELCOME BACK HERE THOUGH.
AFTER ALL,
THIS IS YOUR HOME, RIN.
YEAH. OH, HAVE YOU SEEN
YUKIO AROUND?
HAS HE GONE BACK TO THE DORM?
'CAUSE I CAN'T FIND HIM.
[ MARUTA ] HE'S HERE. WE HAVEN'T
SEEN HIM AROUND THIS MORNING,
BUT HE HASN'T LEFT.
[ CHILD CRYING ]
I'M SO SCARED.
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
HEY.
HUH?
YUKIO, IF YOU WANT,
YOU COULD JOIN ME.
♪ [ MAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ RIN GROWLS ]
SERIOUSLY? THAT GUY
IN THE CLOWN SUIT'S LATE.
AND WHERE THE HELL DID YUKIO GO?
HUH?
[ GASPS, SHOUTS ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ SHRIEKS ]
ARE YOU BLIND?
WHY DON'T YOU WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING, YOU--
WELL, WELL, WELL.
I SEE THE SUN'S OUT.
IT'S A GLORIOUS DAY
FOR NEW BEGINNINGS,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
YOU GOT A FREAKY CAR.
AND IF YOU WANT ME TO GET IN,
TELL ME
WHERE YOU'RE TAKING ME FIRST.
TRUE CROSS ACADEMY. DUH.
T-TRUE CROSS ACADEMY?
INDEED.
YOU SEE, I AM THE DIRECTOR
OF TRUE CROSS ACADEMY.
THAT'S THE OFFICIAL TITLE
ANYWAY.
- HUH?
- ELOQUENTLY SAID.
STARTING TODAY, YOU ARE
A FULL-TIME STUDENT
AT OUR PRESTIGIOUS INSTITUTION.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
I'M SO GLAD THIS WORKED OUT.
THIS WAY YOU AND I
CAN STAY TOGETHER.
YUKIO.
THANK YOU FOR HELPING US OUT,
MR. FAUST.
MR. FAUST?
WHAT HAPPENED TO MEPHISTO?
YES, WELL, OFFICIALLY,
MY NAME IS JOHANN FAUST V.
OFFICIALLY, GET IT?
- HUH?
- AVANTI, GENTLEMEN!
TRUE CROSS ACADEMY AWAITS!
[ WHISTLING ]
[ RIN THINKING ]
WHAT THE HELL?
I THOUGHT I SAID
I WANTED TO BE AN EXORCIST.
DAMN.
HMM?
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, NOTHING.
BY THE WAY, WHERE WERE YOU
THIS MORNING ANYWAY?
VISITING DAD'S GRAVE.
DID YOU GO?
- UH, NO, I DIDN'T.
- TYPICAL YOU.
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
WELL, JUST A FEW MINUTES MORE
AND WE'LL BE IN THE CENTER
OF TRUE CROSS ACADEMY TOWN.
[ MEPHISTO ]
WELCOME TO TRUE CROSS ACADEMY.
HOLY CRAP!
EVERY LEARNING FACILITY
UNDER THE SUN CAN BE FOUND
RIGHT HERE IN ACADEMY TOWN.
ENJOY, DIG IN AND STUDY
TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT.
NOW THEN, RIN,
PLEASE CHANGE INTO YOUR UNIFORM.
OH, COME ON.
NOW YOU'RE TELLING ME?
YOUR TIE-KNOTTING SKILLS
ARE QUITE EXTRAORDINARY.
MAN, I GOT MR. SUSPICIOUS
OVER THERE...
AND YUKIO OVER HERE,
WHO STILL WON'T
ASK ME ANYTHING.
IT'S KIND OF MIND BLOWING,
HUH, YUKIO?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
A DOOFUS LIKE ME
GETTING INTO TRUE CROSS
JUST LIKE YOU.
OH, UH, SORRY.
I'M SO NERVOUS
I WASN'T PAYING ATTENTION.
[ MAN ]
MEET YOUR FRESHMAN CLASS
REPRESENTATIVE, YUKIO OKUMURA.
YES, SIR.
HUH? YUKIO?
[ GIRL ]
THAT MEANS HE GOT THE TOP SCORE
ON THE ENTRANCE EXAM. WOW!
DO YOU SEE HOW HOT HE IS?
[ GIGGLES ]
"TO BE ABLE TO JOIN YOU HERE
AT TRUE CROSS, A SCHOOL
I'VE LONG ADMIRED,
IS SOMETHING THAT IS BOTH
THRILLING AND SOBERING.
YUKIO, THE LITTLE CRYBABY
WHO ALWAYS GOT BULLIED.
...BE DILIGENT,
AND LIVE UP TO THE STANDARDS
OF THIS SPECIAL PLACE.
I'M YOUR FRESHMAN CLASS REP,
YUKIO OKUMURA."
[ CHATTERING ]
[ MAN ]
MAY I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION,
PLEASE.
I'LL BE TAKING YOU
ON A TOUR OF THE CAMPUS
AS PART OF YOUR ORIENTATION.
[ GIRL ]
YUKIO, WHICH CLASS ARE YOU IN?
THE ADVANCED CLASS.
OH, I SHOULD'VE KNOWN!
WOW! YOU'RE SO TALL!
HEY, YOU WANNA BE A DOCTOR
WHEN YOU GROW UP?
I, UH, I GUESS.
THAT'S GREAT!
THAT'S AWESOME!
IF ANYONE CAN BE A DOCTOR,
I KNOW YOU CAN.
HMM? DO YOU REALLY THINK SO?
HECK, YEAH, I THINK SO.
THANKS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S GONNA BE A DOCTOR
SOMEDAY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HE DOESN'T HAVE A CLUE
ABOUT ANYTHING.
AND I'M NOT GONNA
DRAG HIM INTO IT.
NO. IT'S MY PROBLEM.
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
THIS IS A SCHOOL?
WHOA-HO-HO.
WOULD YOU GET A LOAD
OF THOSE CHANDELIERS?
IT'S LIKE A FANCY SCHMANCY
RESTAURANT.
DAMN!
YOU THINK THEY COULD HAVE MADE
THIS ROOM ANY BIGGER?
HELL, EVEN THE DESKS HERE
ARE WAY BIGGER
THAN THE ONES AT THE MONASTERY.
WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THAT GUY?
HE'S FREAKING OUT.
I KNOW. WHAT'S A WEIRDO
LIKE THAT DOING HERE?
UH-- MM.
[ MAN ]
THAT'S ALL FOR TODAY.
CLASSES START NEXT WEEK,
SO YOU SHOULD GO BACK
TO YOUR DORMS
AND GET SETTLED IN.
AFTER JUNIOR HIGH, I WAS JUST
GONNA GET A JOB OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT ANY
OF THIS HIGH SCHOOL B.S.
ALL THAT MATTERS NOW
IS BECOMING AN EXORCIST.
WAIT. WHERE THE HELL'S
THE DORM ANYWAY?
NO ONE TELLS ME JACK
AROUND HERE.
[ WHINING ]
HMM?
[ PANTING ]
WHO LET YOU IN?
[ GROANING ]
WHAT THE--
[ PANTING ]
[ SHOUTS ]
PARDON ME,
BUT IT WOULD BE UNSEEMLY...
FOR THE DIRECTOR OF THE ACADEMY
TO BE CAUGHT PROWLING AROUND
THE HALLS DURING THE DAY.
YOU SHAPE-SHIFTED.
DOES THAT MEAN EXORCISTS
CAN SHAPE-SHIFT?
GOD, NO.
ALTHOUGH I AM AN EXCEPTION.
HA. THAT KEY GRANTS ACCESS
TO THE CRAM SCHOOL
THROUGH ANY DOOR AT ANY TIME.
CRAM SCHOOL?
IT'S WHERE YOU'LL TRAIN
TO BECOME AN EXORCIST.
OH.
EACH DAY YOU'LL ATTEND
NORMAL HIGH SCHOOL CLASSES.
BUT AFTERWARDS YOU'LL TRAIN
AT THE CRAM SCHOOL
TO BECOME A PAGE.
WHILE YOU STUDY EXORCISM,
YOU'LL BE CONSIDERED
AND EXORCIST IN TRAINING.
YOUR HIGH SCHOOL CLASSES
DON'T BEGIN TILL NEXT WEEK.
BUT CRAM SCHOOL?
WELL, THAT STARTS TODAY.
I TRUST
YOU'RE READY TO BEGIN?
NEVER BEEN READIER.
INDEED?
I MUST WARN YOU THOUGH.
IT WOULD BE BEST
IF YOU KEPT THE WHOLE
SON OF SATAN THING CONFIDENTIAL.
SAY WHAT YOU WANT
ABOUT YOUR EARS, FANGS AND TAIL,
BUT THE FLAMES ARE A NO-NO.
CONTROL YOURSELF.
OKAY. I'LL DO MY BEST.
FABULOUS.
VERY WELL, LET'S GET TO IT.
HEY!
NOW THEN, IF YOU'D BE SO KIND,
TRY OPENING ONE OF THESE DOORS
WITH THAT KEY I GAVE YOU.
UH, YEAH, SURE.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, WOW!
THE FRESHMAN CLASS
IS IN ROOM 1106.
THIS WAY.
OKAY.
HERE WE ARE.
OH, AND I'LL BE SITTING IN
WITH YOU TODAY.
OH, SHIT.
NOW I'M GETTING NERVOUS.
EIN, ZWEI, DREI.
HUH?
ALL RIGHTY, LET'S GO.
WAIT! YOU CAN TALK?
YOU'RE SURE YOU WANT TO BE
AN EXORCIST?
YOU BETTER MAKE UP YOUR MIND
BEFORE YOU OPEN THAT DOOR.
[ CREAKING ]
[ THINKING ]
WHAT A DUMP.
[ CLOCK CHIMING ]
I'M RIN OKUMURA.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
[ HUFFS ]
WHAT'S UP WITH THESE GUYS?
THEY'RE EXORCISTS
IN TRAINING,
HERE TO LEARN THE ROPES
JUST LIKE YOU.
SOME OF THEM HAVEN'T RECEIVED
THEIR TEMPTAINTS YET,
WHILE OTHERS HAVE ALREADY
BEEN AFFLICTED.
WHAT'S A TEMPTAINT?
IT'S A WOUND OR A DISEASE
INFLICTED BY DEMONS.
SINCE BEING INFECTED
WITH A TEMPTAINT ENABLES ONE
TO SEE DEMONS,
IT'S SORT OF LIKE
A RITE OF PASSAGE THAT EVERY
EXORCIST MUST UNDERGO.
WELL, IN YOUR CASE, THERE'S
NO NEED FOR IT, IS THERE?
I MEAN, YOU ARE
A DEMON AFTER ALL.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
AH, YOUR INSTRUCTOR
HAS ARRIVED.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ GASPS ]
I'M YOUR INSTRUCTOR.
MY NAME IS YUKIO OKUMURA.
WHAT? YUKIO?
HELLO THERE, EVERYONE.
MY NAME IS YUKIO OKUMURA,
AND I'M THE NEW TEACHER
FOR THE ANTI-DEMON
PHARMACEUTICS CLASS.
NICE TO MEET YOU, MR. OKUMURA.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU,
SIR.
WHAT'S UP, SIR?
WHAT THE HELL,
YUKIO?
I'M SORRY.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YEAH, THERE'S A PROBLEM.
- WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- ALTHOUGH I'M THE SAME AGE
AS MOST OF YOU,
I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU CALLED ME "TEACHER"
WHEN CLASS IS IN SESSION.
I'VE BEEN STUDYING EXORCISM
SINCE I WAS SEVEN,
AND I FINISHED
THE LAST OF MY COURSES
TWO YEARS AGO.
SINCE YOU WERE SEVEN?
YOU'RE KIDDING?
HE HAPPENS TO BE
THE YOUNGEST PERSON IN HISTORY
TO EARN THE RANK OF EXORCIST.
HE'S A GENIUS IN HIS FIELD.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
LET'S GET STARTED.
IS THERE ANYONE IN CLASS
WHO HAS NOT YET RECEIVED
A TEMPTAINT?
OKAY. THREE.
WELL, IN THAT CASE, LET'S START
WITH THE TEMPTAINT RITUAL.
TEMPTAINT RITUAL?
DEMONS WILL BE SUMMONED,
AND YOUR CLASSMATES--
THE ONES WHO HAVEN'T
BEEN AFFLICTED--
WILL RECEIVE THEIR TEMPTAINT.
THE ROOM WE'RE IN
ISN'T NORMALLY USED,
SO GOBLINS MOVED IN.
NOW GOBLINS,
IF YOU DIDN'T ALREADY KNOW,
ARE A TYPE OF DEMON.
[ GIRL ]
HUH? IS THIS PLACE SAFE?
YES, IT'S SAFE.
A GOBLIN IS A LOW-LEVEL DEMON,
A MISCHIEF MAKER,
SO THEY'RE PERFECT
FOR RITUALS LIKE THIS.
YUKIO, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WAIT.
HEY, YUKIO.
CLASS IS IN SESSION.
WOULD YOU PLEASE SIT DOWN?
YOU KNEW ABOUT IT ALL ALONG.
ABOUT DAD... AND ME.
COME ON, YUKIO,
TALK TO ME!
THAT BEING SAID,
IF THEY CATCH THE SCENT
OF ROTTEN ANIMAL BLOOD,
- THEY BECOME EXCITED
AND TURN FEROCIOUS.
- [ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
HOLD UP A SEC.
WE NEED TO TALK, MAN.
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT?
- DON'T PLAY DUMB.
- [ GASPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
FINE. IF THAT'S THE WAY
YOU WANT IT.
SORRY, CLASS, WOULD EVERYONE
PLEASE STEP OUT
AND WAIT IN THE HALL?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DISCUSS
WITH MR. OKUMURA IN PRIVATE.
GEEZ, THAT KID'S
A HUGE PAIN IN THE ASS.
[ GRUMBLING ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
WELL, WE'RE ALONE.
IF YOU WANNA ASK ME SOMETHING,
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE.
WOULD YOU KNOCK IT OFF?
JUST DROP THE ACT.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
WELL, YOU HEARD THE MAN.
EXPLAIN AWAY.
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S LIKE I ALREADY
SAID EARLIER.
I BECAME AN EXORCIST
TWO YEARS AGO.
AND WHEN I WAS SEVEN,
THAT'S WHEN I STARTED TRAINING
FOR IT...
RIGHT AFTER DAD SUGGESTED IT.
THE OLD MAN?
YOU MEAN, YOU'VE KNOWN
ABOUT THE WORK HE WAS DOING?
YOU'VE KNOWN
THIS WHOLE TIME?
I DID.
[ GASPS ]
YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
WHO DIDN'T KNOW, RIN.
I GOT MY TEMPTAINT
WHEN I WAS BORN.
YOU WERE THE DEMON
WHO GAVE IT TO ME.
I'VE BEEN ABLE
TO SEE DEMONS
FOR AS LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER.
NO WAY.
WHAT THE HELL?
WHY'D YOU KEEP IT A SECRET?
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY ANYTHING?
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
ABOUT IT BEFORE?
- LET GO OF ME!
ANSWER ME, YUKIO!
OH, DAMN, THAT STINKS.
- [ SCREECHING ]
- [ GASPS ]
YUKIO?
THOSE ARE HOBGOBLINS, RIN.
AND NOW THAT WE'VE
RILED THEM UP,
THERE'S GOING TO BE MORE.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THEM.
YOU'D BETTER WAIT OUTSIDE.
- BUT I'M NOT DONE YET!
- [ SCREECHING ]
[ SHELLS CLINKING ]
ALL THESE YEARS,
ALL THAT TIME,
WHAT'D YOU THINK
OF ME?
WHAT DID I THINK OF YOU?
- [ SCREECHING ]
- THAT SHOULD BE OBVIOUS.
I MEAN, YOU ARE A DEMON,
AREN'T YOU?
- AS FAR AS I WAS CONCERNED,
YOU WERE A THREAT.
- [ GASPS ]
YOU STILL ARE.
MY GOD, YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT.
AND IT'S A MYSTERY TO ME
WHY YOU EVEN WANT TO BECOME
AN EXORCIST.
FOR REVENGE?
OR MAYBE YOU'RE TRYING
TO WIPE AWAY ALL THE GUILT YOU
FEEL OVER OUR FATHER'S DEATH.
IF THAT'S REALLY
HOW YOU FEEL,
THEN YOU SHOULD SURRENDER
TO THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
BETTER YET, YOU SHOULD JUST DIE.
YOU THINK IT'S MY FAULT
THE OLD MAN DIED?
IS THAT IT?
WOULD I BE WRONG IF I DID?
DAD WAS PROTECTING YOU
THE WHOLE TIME.
EVEN I KNEW THAT.
OUR FATHER WAS THE ONLY PERSON
IN THE WHOLE WORLD...
WHO HAD THE POWER TO RESIST
BEING POSSESSED BY SATAN!
BUT THAT ONLY MADE SATAN WANT
TO POSSESS HIM EVEN MORE.
HIS WILLPOWER WAS THE ONLY THING
KEEPING HIM SAFE
FOR THE LAST 15 YEARS.
OUR FATHER WAS THE MOST POWERFUL
EXORCIST OF ALL!
THERE'S NO WAY
HE'D LET SATAN IN LIKE THAT.
[ SCREECHING ]
SOMETHING MUST HAVE HAPPENED
TO SHATTER HIS SOUL.
TO BREAK HIS HEART.
YOU SAID SOMETHING TO HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?
DON'T EVER LET ME SEE YOU
ACTING LIKE MY FATHER AGAIN!
IF DAD HAD A WEAKNESS,
I'D SAY...
IT WAS YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KILLED OUR FATHER.
LISTEN. YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT ME BEING AN IDIOT.
SAY WHAT YOU WANT.
I DON'T CARE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM STILL YOUR BROTHER,
DAMN IT.
DO NOT POINT YOUR GUN AT ME.
WE'RE BROTHERS!
- [ GASPS ]
- [ EXPLOSIONS ]
[ SCREECHING ]
FOR THE LAST TIME,
I DID NOT KILL THE OLD MAN.
BUT IF YOU REALLY WANT
TO SHOOT ME,
GO AHEAD, SHOOT!
SHOOT!
[ ROARING ]
HUH.
[ GROANING ]
DON'T INSULT ME.
I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT
MY LITTLE BROTHER.
WHAT WAS FATHER LIKE...
BEFORE HE DIED?
HE KICKED ASS.
HE DIED
TRYING TO PROTECT ME
TILL THE END.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHY
I WANNA BE AN EXORCIST?
IT'S NOT ABOUT REVENGE
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I JUST WANNA BE STRONGER.
I WANNA BE STRONG
SO NO ONE ELSE DIES
'CAUSE OF ME!
[ CRYING ]
I'M SO SCARED.
I DON'T WANNA SEE
THESE SCARY THINGS ANYMORE.
HEY.
HUH?
YUKIO, IF YOU WANT,
YOU COULD JOIN ME
AND WE COULD FIGHT TOGETHER.
- OH?
- DO YOU WANT
TO BE AFRAID FOREVER?
OR DO YOU WANT TO BE STRONG
SO YOU CAN PROTECT RIN
AND OTHERS?
PROTECT RIN?
I COULD DO THAT?
YES.
- LIKE ME.
- HUH?
I WANTED TO BE STRONGER TOO,
AND IT'S BECAUSE OF WHAT DAD
SAID TO ME THAT I'M AN EXORCIST.
AND YOU SEE? WE BOTH WANT
THE SAME THING, RIN.
BUT KNOW THIS--
AS LONG AS YOU WANT
TO BECOME AN EXORCIST,
WHAT I SAID EARLIER
WILL FOLLOW YOU
THROUGHOUT YOUR LIFE.
BETTER YET, YOU SHOULD JUST DIE.
EXORCISTS HUNT DEMONS,
SO SOMEONE'S ALWAYS
GOING TO BE GUNNING FOR YOU.
DON'T YOU EVER FORGET THAT,
BIG BROTHER.
GOT IT, TEACHER, SIR.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ YUKIO ]
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING,
CLASS.
SHALL WE CONTINUE OUR LESSON
FOR TODAY?
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED
IN HERE?
WHAT'S UP WITH THE ROOM?
FORGET THE ROOM.
WHAT'S UP WITH THEM?
[ RIN ]
602, 602.
OH, HERE IT IS.
OH. HUH?
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SURPRISE.
I GOT THE SCHOOL
TO BEND SOME RULES
TO LET ME ROOM WITH YOU.
AND IT GETS BETTER--
YOU AND I HAVE THE WHOLE
BUILDING ALL TO OURSELVES.
HEY, YOU'RE DANGEROUS.
SOMEONE'S GOTTA KEEP YOU
UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
HUH? SURVEILLANCE?
AM I IN PRISON OR SOMETHING?
YEP. AND THAT MEANS
I'M THE WARDEN.
YOU WANT TO BECOME
AN EXORCIST, DON'T YOU?
IT'S A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
[ GRUMBLING ]
IF THAT'S HOW IT'S GONNA BE,
OKAY, BRING IT ON.
[ YUKIO ]
THAT'S THE SPIRIT. ALL RIGHT.
NOW, LET'S GET THAT HOMEWORK
I ASSIGNED OUT OF THE WAY.
[ RIN GROWLING ]
H-H-HOMEWORK?
THAT IS WHAT I SAID.
OKAY, OKAY.
STOP HASSLING ME!
♪ [ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ GROANS ]
NOW I'VE GOTTA COME UP
WITH A LESSON PLAN
THAT EVEN HE CAN FOLLOW.
[ GIRL ]
GRANDMA SAID
IT'S A PLACE GOD CREATED...
WHERE HE GATHERED ALL
THE PLANTS IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
[ YUKIO ]
THEY EXPLOIT THE WEAKNESSES
OF A PERSON'S SOUL.
[ GIRL ]
I WON'T LEAVE IT, MOM!
I HATE YOU!
[ RIN ]
WOULD YOU SNAP OUT
OF IT ALREADY?