WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT'S COMING.
[ GRUNTS ]
SHOW YOURSELF!
[ GASPS ]
DAMN YOU!
- FOUL DEMON.
- [ GASPS ]
LEAVE THIS WORLD.
YOU DON'T BELONG HERE!
[ GRUNTS ]
IZUMO!
WHAT?
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
- UKE! MIKE!
- [ ROARING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
♪ [ MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SHIEMI ]
GOOD MORNING.
HEY.
[ SWEEPING ]
HUH?
[ SHIMA ]
OKAY, WHATCHA DOING?
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
WE'RE CLEANING UP.
SHOULDN'T YOU GUYS
BE HEADING OVER TO CLASS NOW?
WHAT, YOU DIDN'T GET
THE E-MAIL?
HUH?
[ BEEPING ]
I SENT THAT
TO ALL THE EXORCISTS
IN OUR REGION.
I'M AFRAID IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
WHY'D YOU SEND IT TO US?
WE'RE JUST EXWIRES.
THE SITUATION IS SO DIRE,
MY BOY, THAT I FELT WE NEEDED
YOUR ASSISTANCE AS WELL.
A TYPE OF DEMON CALLED GUFU
HAS MANAGED TO INFILTRATE
THE ACADEMY.
SIR PHELES'S PROTECTIVE BARRIER
IS SUPPOSED TO REPEL ANY DEMON
THAT'S MID-LEVEL OR HIGHER,
SO WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
HOW IT GOT IN HERE.
A DEMON CAN ONLY CIRCUMVENT
THE BARRIER ONE OF TWO WAYS.
EITHER THE BARRIER
HAS A TEAR IN IT
SOMEWHERE...
OR THERE IS A PERSON
INSIDE THE ACADEMY
WHO LET THE DEMON IN.
SAY WHAT?
WHO'D DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT AND WHY?
WHO KNOWS?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
NOW, THEN, I'VE ASKED
THE INSTRUCTORS TO INVESTIGATE
THE GUFU'S WHEREABOUTS.
HOWEVER, I'D LIKE YOU EXWIRES
TO PERSONALLY CONDUCT
AN INSPECTION OF THE BARRIER.
[ ALL ]
YES, SIR.
[ GRUNTS ]
NOT YOU, RIN.
YOU'RE STAYING HERE
AND TRAINING SOME MORE.
WHA--
THAT SEAL LOOKS GOOD.
YEAH.
THAT'S ANOTHER ONE.
HEY, HOW MANY
OF THESE BARRIERS
ARE THERE TOTAL?
[ GRUNTS ]
12,000.
[ GROANS ]
OH, MAN. THAT NUMBER
MAKES MY HEAD SPIN.
[ GROANS ]
WE'RE GONNA NEED
ALL THE HELP WE CAN
JUST TO GET THROUGH THIS THING.
WHERE THE HECK'S KONEKO AT?
HE SHOULD BE HELPING.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT BY THE TIME
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING,
HE'D ALREADY LEFT THE DORM.
I'VE BEEN CALLING HIS CELL,
BUT HE'S NOT PICKING IT UP.
HE DIDN'T WANNA COME WITH US
WHEN WE WENT TO FIX KURKIKARA.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE'S THINKING ABOUT
QUITTING THE CRAM SCHOOL.
OH, YEAH?
LIKE HELL HE IS!
HE MADE A PROMISE, REMEMBER?
SATAN KILLED HIS FAMILY,
AND HE WAS GONNA GET REVENGE
FOR 'EM.
BON.
HE'D NEVER GO BACK
ON HIS WORD.
NO WAY.
[ WINGS FLAPPING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GUFU ]
DOES IT HURT?
O-OF COURSE IT DOES.
I GOT SHOT.
[ GROANING ]
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ACCEPT ME
AND BULLETS WILL NEVER HURT.
WHY DO YOU REJECT ME?
IF YOU HAD MY POWER,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO FEAR
THE SON OF SATAN ANYMORE.
COME. FIGHT WITH ME.
WE SHALL KILL
THE SON OF SATAN TOGETHER.
NO WAY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WANT.
I NEVER WANTED THAT.
I COULD NEVER KILL OKUMURA.
WHY DOES RIN OKUMURA HAVE TO BE
IN THE SAME CLASS AS ME?
[ GASPS ]
WILL HE TAKE AWAY MY FRIENDS
LIKE HIS FATHER TOOK MY FAMILY?
OKUMURA.
HOW DARE HE, HOW DARE HE,
HOW DARE HE, HOW DARE HE!
YOU'RE WRONG!
STOP IT!
[ LAUGHING ]
ACCEPT THE DARKNESS
IN YOUR SOUL.
I'LL LEND YOU MY POWER ANYTIME
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WISH.
[ GUFU LAUGHING ]
WHERE AM I?
I'VE GOTTA GET BACK.
EVERYONE MUST BE WORRIED
ABOUT ME.
NOTHING TASTES BETTER
THAN REVENGE WHEN YOUR SOUL
IS FILLED WITH HATE.
THAT'S MY CHANCE TO HARVEST IT.
[ RIN GRUNTING ]
[ GROANS ]
COME ON, HOW LONG
AM I SUPPOSED
TO KEEP DOING THIS?
YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP DOING IT
UNTIL YOU FIGURE OUT HOW
TO CONTROL YOUR FLAMES BETTER.
[ GROANS, BLOWS ]
ARE YOU COOL WITH THIS?
SITTING AROUND WHEN THERE'S
A DEMON TO HUNT?
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'D RATHER BE OUT THERE
TRYING TO FIND THE GUFU.
BUT I'VE BEEN ORDERED
TO KEEP AN EYE ON YOU,
SO I DON'T REALLY HAVE A CHOICE.
WELL, THEN, LET'S BAIL
AND GO HUNTING.
COME ON.
WOULD YOU BE SERIOUS
FOR ONCE?
YOU'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME HERE, RIN.
IF YOU THINK EVERYTHING'S
GONNA GO YOUR WAY LIKE IT
ALWAYS HAS, THEN YOU NEED--
- [ GROANS ]
- [ GASPS ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S NOTHING.
JUST KEEP GOING
WITH YOUR TRAINING.
[ SIGHS ]
YES, SIR.
YEAH, RIGHT, SUCKA.
THE BEST WAY TO IMPROVE
MY SKILLS IS BY GETTING OUT
INTO THE FIELD.
[ SHOUTING, GRUNTS ]
[ GROANING ]
IT'S NOT WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE, YUKIO.
I SWEAR I WASN'T THINKING
OF DITCHING.
OH, MAN.
YOU SCARED ME.
[ GASPS ]
[ JINGLING ]
[ SHIMA ] MAN, MY FEET
ARE ALL SWOLLEN.
- OH, HEY, TEACH.
- HOW'S IT GOING THERE?
YOU SURVIVING THIS HEAT?
I JUST WASHED MY FACE,
AND IT HELPED A LITTLE.
NEED COLD WATER.
WE CHECKED THE BARRIERS
ON THE WEST SIDE,
AND THEY'RE ALL GOOD.
SO ARE THE ONES
AT THE MAIN GATE.
GREAT JOB.
THANK YOU.
[ SCREAMING ]
HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED?
HEY, WAIT.
HOLD UP, YOU GUYS.
[ GASPING ]
KONEKOMARU! WHAT HAPPENED?
AH! I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S OKUMURA.
HE JUST CAME AFTER ME.
HUH?
WATCH OUT, SUGURO.
GET AWAY FROM HIM.
HE'S DANGEROUS.
YOU DUMBASS.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S DANGEROUS AROUND HERE.
[ GUFU LAUGHING ]
DAMN IT,
DON'T YOU LAUGH AT ME!
[ MIWA WHIMPERING ]
OKUMURA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
I'M GONNA SLASH ITS ASS.
RIN, STAND DOWN
AND GET AWAY FROM HIM.
WHY ARE YOU POINTING
THAT GUN AT ME?
THERE'S YOUR TARGET.
WHAT THE--
WHOA, COULD YOU GUYS
JUST CHILL?
COME ON,
PUT THOSE THINGS AWAY, HUH?
[ GUFU LAUGHING ]
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
- NO, RIN!
- [ GASPING ]
HEY! ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CONTROL YOURSELF.
IF YOU GO ON ANOTHER RAMPAGE,
THEY'RE GO--
[ GRUNTS ]
I ALREADY TOLD YOU
ONCE, OKUMURA.
IF YOU EVER HURT
ANY OF MY FRIENDS,
I SWORE I'D KILL YOU.
DAMN IT, ARE YOU BLIND
OR SOMETHING?
I WAS GOING AFTER THE DEMON.
[ SHIMA ]
KONEKO.
COME ON, WAKE UP, KONEKO.
WHAT DO WE DO?
HE'S NOT WAKING UP?
DON'T WORRY.
HE'S FINE.
HE'S UNCONSCIOUS,
THAT'S ALL.
OH.
THOSE DAMN FLAMES OF YOURS
COULD KILL PEOPLE, YOU JERK.
[ GASPS ]
WHY CAN'T YOU GET THAT
THROUGH YOUR HEAD ALREADY?
GET OUT OF HERE.
[ METALLIC CLANGING ]
[ SLITHERING ]
[ HISSING ]
[ RATTLING ]
LOOKS LIKE HE FOUND SOMETHING.
[ SHURA ]
IS THAT IT?
[ TSUBAKI ]
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
YOU KNOW GUFUS
ARE TROUBLESOME DEMONS.
YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
WHAT THE HELL?
I ABSOLUTELY DO NOT LIKE
THE LOOK OF THIS.
AND I BET AN ACADEMY KEY
WAS USED TO OPEN IT.
IF THIS DOOR CLOSES,
WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO GET BACK,
AND I'LL NEVER SEE
MY KITTY CAT AGAIN.
WELL, YOU GOT A POINT.
WHY DON'T YOU HANG OUT HERE
AND HOLD IT OPEN?
WAIT!
MISS KIRIGAKURE!
COME BACK!
[ SHIVERING ]
DAMN, IT'S SO COLD.
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS PLACE?
[ GROANING ]
[ SUGURO ]
HEY, YOU'RE UP.
BON!
[ GROANS ]
EASY. YOU'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
[ GROANS ]
- WHERE AM I?
- YOU'RE AT TRUE CROSS
GENERAL HOSPITAL.
ANYWAY, I DIDN'T SEE YOU
ALL DAY, SO I WAS WONDERING,
WHERE THE HECK
DID YOU DISAPPEAR TO?
[ GROANING ]
I CAN'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
YEAH, OKAY.
JUST TRY TO GET
SOME REST TONIGHT,
AND BY TOMORROW YOU SHOULD BE
GOOD AS NEW.
BON.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S ABOUT OKUMURA.
I-- WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT HIM?
WHAT DO I THINK?
ABOUT THAT IDIOT?
HUH?
AFTER ALL THE CRAP HE'S PULLED,
THAT JERK GOES
AND ASKS ME TO TRUST HIM.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT SOMEONE
TO TRUST YOU, Y-Y-YOU KNOW,
YOU--
YOU GOTTA HAVE
SOMETHING MORE THAN THAT.
BUT THAT GUY,
HE'S GOT NOTHING ELSE
TO OFFER.
[ EXHALES ]
I'M SCARED.
JUST KNOWING THERE'S SOMEONE
LIKE OKUMURA OUT THERE
TERRIFIES ME.
AH, HE'S NOTHING
BUT A MORON.
I MEAN, SURE, HIS POWER CAN BE
PRETTY SCARY, BUT IN THE END,
THAT GUY?
NAH, HE'S ABOUT
AS CLUELESS AS THEY COME.
IT'S SILLY
TO BE SCARED OF HIM.
BUT IS THAT THE PROBLEM?
- MAYBE YOU WANNA QUIT.
- [ GASPS ]
YOU WANT ME TO REMIND YOU
ABOUT WHY YOU CAME HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
YOU HEARD THE STORY
ABOUT HOW YOUR MOM WAS BURNED
ALIVE BY THE BLUE FLAMES.
HOW SHE WAS PREGNANT WITH YOU
AND PROTECTED YOU
TO HER LAST BREATH.
SHE DIED PROTECTING YOU.
SHE LOVED YOU THAT MUCH.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
I KNOW.
I JUST CAN'T--
[ SIGHS ]
I'M HEADING OUT.
STILL GOT ABOUT 6,000
BARRIERS TO CHECK.
UH, BON.
YOUR SHIRT--
WHAT HAPPENED TO IT?
HUH? OH, THAT.
WAS IT WHEN--
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS BUY ANOTHER SHIRT.
IT'S COOL.
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ GUFU ]
YOU SEE?
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU DON'T DO AS I ASK.
HE IS STILL DANGEROUS.
THE TRAGEDY OF THE BLUE NIGHT
WILL BE REPEATED.
NO.
YOUR FRIENDS ARE PRECIOUS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOSE THEM,
DO YOU?
ACCEPT ME. NOW.
THEN YOU MUST KILL HIM.
YOU MUST KILL THE SON OF SATAN.
[ WHIMPERING ]
- [ SCREAMING ]
- [ GRUNTS ]
WHAT THE--
[ GASPS ]
KONEKOMARU!
HEY, BON. I JUST GOT BACK
FROM THE CONVENIENCE STORE
DOWN THE HILL.
I FIGURED KONEKO
WAS GETTING BORED,
SO I GOT SOME STUFF
TO STIMULATE
THAT BIG BRAIN OF HIS.
THERE'S NO TIME
FOR THAT!
HUH?
KONEKOMARU'S BEING POSSESSED
BY A DEMON.
HUH?
I'M GOING AFTER HIM.
GO GET MR. OKUMURA.
HURRY.
HEY! WAIT UP, BON!
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ SUGURO ]
THOSE DAMN FLAMES OF YOURS
COULD KILL PEOPLE, YOU JERK.
WHY CAN'T YOU GET THAT
THROUGH YOUR HEAD ALREADY?
[ RIN, THINKING ]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
WHY AM I ALWAYS DOING THIS?
[ WIND BLOWING ]
[ GASPS ]
IT'S YOU.
[ GROWLS ]
GREAT.
WHERE IS HE NOW?
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
YES.
OKUMURA SPEAKING.
WAIT. MIWA'S WHAT?
RIN!
DIE, DEVIL SPAWN!
[ GROANS ]
- KONEKOMARU!
- MIWA! HOLD IT!
SHUT UP!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
IT'S A WIND BARRIER.
YES. BEHOLD MY NEW POWER.
I'VE BEEN REBORN
FOR ONE PURPOSE--
TO RID THE WORLD
OF THE SON OF SATAN!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
DAMN IT!
HOW AM I GONNA STOP IT?
[ GROANING ]
DAMN DEMON.
I'M GOING TO SNAP
THAT NECK OF YOURS.
[ SUGURO ]
HOLD UP, YOU MORON.
GO ON. TAKE A GOOD LOOK
AT YOURSELF.
YOU TELL ME--
WHO'S THE REAL DEMON HERE?
SHUT UP!
I'M FIGHTING TO PROTECT YOU.
TO PROTECT EVERYONE!
OH, PISS OFF!
NOBODY ASKED YOU TO.
COME ON, WAKE UP, KONEKOMARU!
BON.
DON'T BE DECEIVED BY HIM.
THAT BOY IS JEALOUS
OF YOUR POWER.
JEALOUS! HURRY NOW.
KILL HIM.
KILL THE SON OF SATAN!
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ RIN ]
CUT THE CRAP.
I DON'T WANT THIS.
I NEVER ASKED
TO BE THE SON OF SATAN!
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
KONEKOMARU,
IF YOU WANNA BE AFRAID OF ME,
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
THING IS, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
THINKING TRUSTING THIS DEMON?
THAT'S WHAT YOU GOT
YOUR FRIENDS FOR.
SHIMA AND SUGURO.
YOUR FRIENDS GOT YOUR BACK,
NOT THAT THING!
[ MIWA, THINKING ]
WHAT AM I DOING?
EVEN IF I KILL OKUMURA,
IT'S NOT GOING TO BRING BACK
MY MOM AND DAD.
I'M--
- [ GROANS ]
- DAMN YOU!
[ GASPS ]
WHERE'S HE GOING?
KONEKO!
I WON'T LET YOU ESCAPE.
YOU BELONG TO ME!
[ ROARING ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
RIN, STOP IT!
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M GONNA SAVE HIM.
[ BOTH GASP ]
COME ON, KONEKOMARU!
[ GASPS ]
COME ON, JUMP!
TRUST ME!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ BOTH SHOUTING ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
KONEKO!
KONEKOMARU,
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ GROANS ]
BON, SHIMA.
- [ BOTH SIGH ]
- [ CRYING ]
[ YUKIO ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M GOOD.
NO BIG DEAL.
[ MIWA ]
OKUMURA.
HUH?
[ CRYING ]
I'M SORRY I TRIED TO--
I'M SO SORRY.
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
[ MEPHISTO ]
SO IN THE END,
RIN OKUMURA SAVED MIWA.
ANYONE ELSE HURT?
WELL, SUGURO AND SHIMA.
A FEW BRUISES, THAT'S ALL.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
ALTHOUGH I'M STILL CONCERNED
ABOUT HOW THE DEMON
GOT THROUGH THE BARRIER.
WELL, THE ONLY WAY IT COULD
IS IF SOMEONE USED A KEY
TO OPEN A DOORWAY.
PRETTY OBVIOUS, REALLY.
THEN THE SITUATION
IS WORSE THAN I THOUGHT.
ONLY A SELECT FEW ARE ALLOWED
THE USE OF MY KEYS, SO NOW
I'M REALLY CONCERNED.
ME AND TSUBAKI FOUND THE DOORWAY
IN A PARKING LOT IN TOWN.
I WENT THROUGH IT AND FOUND
A TORCHED RESEARCH LAB
IN THIS BIG FOREST.
- THAT'S SUSPICIOUS.
- UH-HUH.
AND IT WASN'T YOUR TYPICAL
RESEARCH LAB EITHER.
THEY WERE EXPERIMENTING
WITH ARTIFICIAL LIFE OUT THERE,
SOMETHING THE VATICAN OUTLAWED
FOR THE LAST THREE CENTURIES.
[ MEPHISTO ]
REALLY?
NOW THAT IS INTRIGUING.
WE SHOULD OPEN AN INVESTIGATION
INTO IT IMMEDIATELY.
KONEKO, YOU'VE GOT
SOME VISITORS.
LOOK, I EVEN BROUGHT
SOME FINE LADIES ALONG
TO CHEER YOU--
HUH?
[ KAMIKI ]
AND HE'S NOT HERE.
I WONDER WHERE
HE'S GONE OFF TO.
[ GASPS ]
DON'T TELL ME
HE'S THINKING ABOUT--
[ GRUNTS ]
[ VEHICLE APPROACHING ]
COME ON, STOP MESSING ARO--
WHAT UP?
O-OKUMURA.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING
WITH THAT GINORMOUS BAG?
YOU DOING LAUNDRY?
UH, UH--
WHAT DO YOU CARE
WHERE I'M GOING?
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS.
HUH?
AFTER MY PARENTS DIED,
I WAS ALL ALONE IN THE WORLD.
THE HEAD MONK AT THE TEMPLE
TOOK ME IN AND RAISED ME
LIKE HIS OWN.
I ALWAYS APPRECIATED
HIS KINDNESS, SO I MADE UP
MY MIND I'D PAY HIM BACK.
THAT'S WHY I CAME
TO THE ACADEMY WITH BON.
TRUTH IS, I'M JUST
A SCAREDY CAT.
I'M TOTALLY USELESS,
SO I DECIDED TO QUIT.
I'M ONLY GONNA GET
IN EVERYONE'S WAY IF I STAY HERE
ONE MINUTE LONGER.
BACK UP.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
THAT I'LL BE IN EVERYONE'S WAY.
NO. BEFORE THAT.
I'M USELESS?
BEFORE THAT!
HUH?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SAID IT'S NONE
OF MY BUSINESS, DIDN'T YOU?
HUH? THAT-THAT FAR?
DON'T SAY IT'S NOT
MY BUSINESS.
IT IS, 'CAUSE BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I THINK OF YOU AS MY FRIEND.
OKUMURA.
AND I'D BE SAD
IF MY FRIEND LEFT, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE LYING.
NO, I'M NOT.
STOP TRYING
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
SUGARCOATING IT
IS NOT GONNA CHANGE THE FACT
THAT I TRIED TO KILL YOU.
AND IF I GET POSSESSED
BY ANOTHER DEMON,
WHO'S TO SAY I WON'T TRY AGAIN?
THAT'S NOT WHAT FRIENDS DO,
SO HOW CAN YOU THINK OF ME
AS YOUR FRIEND?
I KNOW, BUT YOU HAD FAITH
IN ME BACK THERE, REMEMBER?
YOU DID.
AND I HAVE FAITH IN YOU TOO.
THAT'S WHAT BEING FRIENDS
IS ALL ABOUT, ISN'T IT?
[ GASPS ]
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT SOMEONE
TO TRUST YOU, Y-Y-YOU KNOW,
YOU--
YOU GOTTA HAVE
SOMETHING MORE THAN THAT.
BUT THAT GUY, HE'S GOT
NOTHING ELSE TO OFFER.
WOW, IT'S JUST LIKE BON SAID.
YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING ELSE TO OFFER,
DO YOU?
HUH? HEY, MAN,
THAT'S KINDA RUDE.
I GOT LOTS TO OFFER.
LIKE MONEY.
NO.
TALENT?
YEAH, NO.
[ SUGURO ] KONEKOMARU,
WHERE IN THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
BON! HI, GUYS!
HEY! DON'T GO
SWOOPING IN LIKE THAT.
WE'RE HAVING A MOMENT HERE.
[ SHIEMI ]
WHY IS HE SO ANGRY?
[ SUGURO ]
IGNORE HIM.
STUPIDITY'S CONTAGIOUS.
DON'T CALL ME STUPID.
[ SHIMA ]
YOU STILL GOT SOME HEALING
TO DO, KONEKO.
OKUMURA CAN TAKE YOUR BAGS UP
FOR YOU.
[ RIN ]
WHY DO I HAVE TO?
[ KAMIKI ]
IT'S THE LEAST YOU CAN DO.
YOU ARE HIS FRIEND, AREN'T YOU?
GUESS I'M STUCK
WITH 'EM THEN.
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ RIN ]
DO ME.
TELL MY FORTUNE NEXT.
[ SHIMA ]
NOPE. DOESN'T WORK
FOR GUYS.
HOW COME?
I'M A SPECIALIST.
GIRL FORTUNES ONLY.
[ KAMIKI GIGGLING ]
THANK YOU, SHIMA.
YOU'RE SWEET.