[ MAN ]
ETERNAL LIFE YOU SAY?
[ MEPHISTO ]
CORRECT. YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO EXPERIENCE...
ALL THE PLEASURES AND SORROWS
THIS WORLD HAS TO OFFER...
THROUGHOUT ETERNITY EVER AFTER.
BUT IF YOU GROW TIRED
OF YOUR IMMORTALITY
AND WISH FOR IT TO END,
THEN I BECOME THE NEW OWNER
OF YOUR POOR SOUL.
ARE THOSE TERMS ACCEPTABLE?
INTERESTING.
VERY WELL.
I ACCEPT YOUR WAGER.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
THE CONTRACT IS SEALED.
NOW THEN,
I BID YOU ADIEU.
EINS, ZWEI, DREI.
♪ [ MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ ROARING ]
- [ GRUNTS ]
- RIN!
I'M GOOD.
JUST A LITTLE SCRATCH,
IS ALL.
[ GRUNTING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S A DIMENSIONAL TEAR.
MY GUESS IS HE'S EXPANDING
THE GATE TILL IT'S BIG ENOUGH
TO SWALLOW ASSIAH.
I'VE BEEN DREAMING
OF THIS MOMENT
FOR THE LAST 15 YEARS.
THE DAY I FINALLY GET TO BRING
THE WORLDS OF ASSIAH AND GEHENNA
TOGETHER AND CREATE A NEW EARTH.
[ THINKING ]
WE CAN'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
WE HAVE TO STOP HIM.
- [ GROWLING ]
- [ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
RIN! YUKI!
[ ROARING ]
- WATCH OUT!
- SHIEMI!
WHAT THE--
TO YOU, VILLAINS
WHO WOULD CRUSH
INNOCENT FLOWERS SUCH AS THESE,
I, ARTHUR AUGUSTE ANGEL,
SHALL DELIVER JUSTICE.
IT TOOK YA LONG ENOUGH,
BALDY!
I CAN HANDLE THIS ONE.
JUST SIT BACK
AND WATCH THE FIREWORKS.
HEY, DON'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO!
ZODIAC SLASH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SHOUTING ]
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
DAMN IT.
SEPARATE HITS WON'T WORK.
WE HAVE TO TIME OUR ATTACKS.
YUKIO'S RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
WE GOTTA WORK AS A TEAM
OR WE'LL NEVER BREAK THROUGH
THAT PROTECTIVE WALL OF STEEL.
SURE YOU'RE UP FOR IT?
WORRY ABOUT YOURSELF, KID.
I'M NOT AS THRASHED
AS YOU THINK I AM.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D JOIN
FORCES WITH THE SONS OF SATAN.
HOW REVOLTING.
KIRIGAKURE SWORD TECHNIQUE,
SNAKE BELLY!
- [ SNARLING ]
- SNAKE FANG!
ZODIAC SLASH!
WHAT THE--
[ SHOUTING ]
WE DID IT!
[ GASPS ]
[ CRACKING ]
THE HELL?
IMPOSSIBLE.
[ CRASH ]
[ GASPS ]
RIN!
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
[ GASPS ]
RIN!
[ FOOTSTEPS RUNNING ]
DID YOU FIND MORIYAMA?
NOT YET.
THERE'S TOO MANY PEOPLE.
DO YOU THINK SHE COULD BE
OUTSIDE WITH OKUMURA?
HUH?
[ POUNDING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
[ WHIMPERING ]
THE BARRIER'S
BEEN COMPROMISED.
WHOEVER'S AN EXORCIST,
START KILLING THOSE DEMONS.
THE REST OF YOU,
GET AS FAR BACK AS YOU CAN.
DAMN IT.
THIS PLACE IS SUPPOSED
TO BE PROTECTED.
HOW THE HELL'D THEY GET IN HERE?
I-I DON'T KNOW.
YOU THINK OKUMURA'S OKAY?
OF COURSE HE'S OKAY.
THAT GUY, YOU COULD KILL HIM,
BUT HE JUST KEEPS COMING BACK.
[ RIN ]
YUKIO, YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE GATE?
IT'S ATTACKING THE CITY.
I'M SORRY IT GOT TO THIS.
WHAT?
IT'S MY FAULT. EVERYTHING.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
YEAH, YOU MADE SOME MISTAKES,
AND YOU'RE SELFISH AND STUBBORN.
HELL, YOU DON'T EVEN LOOK UP
TO YOUR BIG BROTHER.
MAN, YOU REALLY SUCK.
[ GASPS ]
GROWING UP, YOU NEVER SAID
A DAMN THING
ABOUT SEEING DEMONS.
PLUS, YOU'RE THIS TEACHER,
AND A FREAKING PALADIN?
YOU KNOW, HAVING A SUPER SMART
LITTLE BROTHER LIKE YOU
HAS BEEN A HUGE PAIN THE ASS.
- OW!
- HAVE A LITTLE FAITH
IN ME...
LIKE YOU DID WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
I WILL.
[ KURO ]
RIN!
KURO, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
ALL THIS TIME?
SORRY. I WON'T RUN AWAY AGAIN.
AFTER ALL, I WAS THE FAMILIAR
OF SHIRO, THE MOST POWERFUL
EXORCIST EVER.
GET ON, RIN.
RIGHT.
I'LL GO TOO.
HUH?
NO WAY.
YOU HEARD?
MY DEMONIC POWERS
HAVE BEEN AWAKENED TOO.
NOW I CAN HEAR KURO
LOUD AND CLEAR JUST LIKE YOU.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
MAY I?
OKAY, LET'S ALL GO.
THE DEMON SPAWN
ARE GOING FORTH.
[ SHURA ]
DROP THE DEMON-HUMAN STUFF.
THOSE KIDS ARE FIGHTING HARD
BECAUSE ASSIAH'S THE PLACE
THEY CALL HOME.
IT'S THE PLACE
WHERE SHIRO RAISED 'EM.
[ THINKING ]
YUKI, RIN, PLEASE.
COME BACK SAFE.
[ BUZZING ]
[ CLAMORING ]
THIS WAY!
HURRY!
DAMN IT.
THESE THINGS
JUST KEEP COMING.
I HOPE RIN
AND THE OTHERS
ARE ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SURVIVE THIS, AND WE CAN
WORRY ABOUT THE OTHERS LATER.
LET'S GO.
[ MAN ]
THE STRANGE BLACK MIST,
WHICH APPEARED THIS EVENING...
AROUND TRUE CROSS ACADEMY,
HAS YET TO DISPERSE.
AN EVACUATION HAS BEEN ISSUED
TO ALL RESIDENTS LIVING WITHIN
A 20-KILOMETER RADIUS--
[ THINKING ]
EVEN IF I WENT THERE NOW,
I WOULDN'T BE
MUCH HELP TO THEM.
I'M BETTER OFF STAYING HERE
DOING WHAT I DO BEST.
GOD OF THE IRONWORKS,
PLEASE WATCH OVER RYU
AND THE OTHERS FOR ME.
[ GUNFIRE ]
THERE'S NO END
TO THESE THINGS.
JUST HANG IN THERE,
EVERYONE.
THE LIGHT OF THE MORNING SUN
WILL MAKE THE DEMONS WEAK.
WE'VE GOT TO HOLD OUT
UNTIL THEN.
TILL MORNING?
BUT THE SUN ONLY
JUST WENT DOWN, MAN.
WE CAN'T KEEP THIS UP
FOR LONG.
UM, EXCUSE ME, SIR.
YES, MIWA.
WHAT IS IT?
THE JAPAN BRANCH
IS SUPPOSED TO BE CONNECTED
TO VATICAN HEADQUARTERS, RIGHT?
YEAH. SO WHAT ARE
YOU GETTING AT?
THE TIME DIFFERENCE BETWEEN HERE
AND THE VATICAN IS SEVEN HOURS.
HUH? YEAH!
OH!
OH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "OH"?
I'M TOTALLY LOST HERE.
IF WE USE A MAGIC KEY,
WE CAN EVACUATE TO THE VATICAN.
SINCE IT'S STILL THE MIDDLE
OF THE DAY OVER THERE--
OH.
[ PANTING ]
[ SHIMA ]
AH, YEAH! THE SUN!
[ PAKU ]
GREAT IDEA, MIWA.
NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS FIGURE OUT HOW TO LURE
THE DEMONS INTO THIS SQUARE.
ACTUALLY, WE DON'T NEED 'EM
TO COME HERE.
HUH?
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
[ ROARING ]
DAMN IT.
WATCH OUT!
HANG ON TIGHT!
WHOA!
THANKS A LOT, KURO.
HEY, RIN, FOCUS YOUR ATTACK
ON THE GATE.
WITH THEM IN THE WAY?
THEY'RE JUST GONNA BLOCK
MY SHOT AGAIN.
[ SHIMA ]
CREATE A SUN?
[ SUGURO ]
WE'RE GONNA DIRECT THE SUNLIGHT
FROM HERE TO THE JAPAN BRANCH.
THAT WAY WE CAN HELP
EVERYONE THERE...
AND KEEP THOSE THINGS
FROM GETTING TO EVERYONE
HERE AT THE VATICAN.
- WE'RE READY OVER HERE!
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO THIS.
[ GASPING ]
HERE IT COMES!
TAKE COVER!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT LIGHT?
PRETTY.
[ SHRIEKING ]
THEY'RE DISTRACTED
BY THE LIGHT.
NOW, RIN!
GOT IT!
HERE GOES NOTHING!
[ SHOUTING ]
- RIN!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
YUKIO!
GRAB ON!
WOW!
- THEY'RE FLYING.
- BRAVO! MAGNIFICENT!
I NEVER DREAMED
THEY'D BE ABLE TO CONTROL
THEIR FLAMES LIKE THAT.
BROTHERS OKUMURA,
YOU ARE EXTRAORDINARY!
YOU READY FOR THIS?
YEAH, LET'S TRASH THAT GATE.
[ BOTH SHOUTING ]
[ SATAN ]
WHY WOULD MY SONS--
MINE AND YURI'S OWN
FLESH AND BLOOD--
WHY WOULD YOU DESTROY OUR DREAM?
WE DON'T GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT YOUR DREAM!
WE JUST WANNA PROTECT--
THE PEOPLE WE CARE ABOUT.
AND THE WORLD WE LIVE IN!
[ BOTH ]
WE'LL ALWAYS PROTECT THEM!
[ SATAN SCREAMING ]
[ GASPING ]
WHAT'S THAT LIGHT?
IT'S WARM, ISN'T IT?
[ THINKING ]
RIN, YUKI.
[ YURI ]
SATAN.
[ SATAN ]
YURI, FORGIVE ME.
I COULDN'T MAKE
YOUR DREAM COME TRUE.
YOU WERE TOO IMPATIENT.
NEITHER OF US KNOWS
IF THE PATH WE CHOSE
WAS THE RIGHT ONE.
THAT'S SOMETHING
FOR OUR CHILDREN
TO FIND OUT FOR US.
[ SHIMA ]
MAN, WHAT A MESS.
[ KAMIKI ]
EVERYTHING'S RUINED.
DO YOU THINK
IT'S ALL OVER?
[ RIN ]
HEY, GUYS!
[ PAKU ]
OKUMURA!
- WHAT UP?
- HEY, THEY'RE ALIVE.
YOU MADE IT BACK
IN ONE PIECE.
YOU ARE SUCH
A FRIGGIN' DUMBASS!
YOU LIKE MAKING US WORRY
ABOUT YOU OR SOMETHING?
[ GASPING ]
WHAT HAPPENED TO SATAN?
HE DEAD?
HE WENT BACK TO GEHENNA,
I GUESS.
BUT THERE'S
A CHANCE
HE'LL BE BACK.
WHO KNOWS?
OH, YEAH?
[ SHIEMI ]
RIN, YUKI!
SHIEMI.
WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU TWO THINKING?
- HOW COULD YOU BE
SO RECKLESS?
- [ BOTH ] WHOA! BUSTED!
[ BOTH GASP ]
DO ME A FAVOR.
DON'T MAKE ME WORRY
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
WE WON'T.
I PROMISE.
WHAT ARE YOU,
OUR MOM?
[ SHIEMI CRYING ]
TYPICAL!
YOU GUYS ARE ALWAYS
CAUSING TROUBLE.
TAKARA?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
THIS WHOLE TIME?
[ AMAIMON ]
THE MINIATURE WORLD
YOU LOVE SO MUCH...
HAS BEEN DESTROYED,
BIG BROTHER.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NO, I WAS JUST REMEMBERING
SOMETHING.
A WAGER I HAD
AND THE MAN WHO ACCEPTED IT
A FEW HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
- WHAT WAGER?
- IT WAS EXTRAORDINARY.
THE STAKES WERE LIFE
OR DEATH.
WHICH OF YOU WON?
I DID, OF COURSE.
I'M THINKING ABOUT WHAT HE SAID
WHEN HE DIED THOUGH.
HE SHOUTED, "STOP, TIME!
THOU ART SO BEAUTIFUL!"
THE WAY YOU FELT
AT THAT MOMENT, SIR,
I BELIEVE I NOW UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU MEANT.
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ RIN ]
A MONTH WENT BY,
AND HERE WE ARE.
MEPHISTO--
UH, SCRATCH THAT.
JOHANN FAUST V
WAS BROUGHT BACK
AS DIRECTOR OF THE ACADEMY.
THEY STARTED CLASSES
BACK UP AGAIN TOO.
[ YUKIO ] THE MANDRAKE HAS
BEEN USED AS AN APHRODISIAC
SINCE THE DAYS BEFORE CHRIST.
THE ROOT IS SHAPED LIKE A HUMAN.
NOW YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
WHEN PULLING THE MANDRAKE
OUT OF THE GROUND...
BECAUSE ONCE IT'S OUT--
[ RIN ]
FOR SOME REASON THEY TOOK AWAY
YUKIO'S RANK AS PALADIN.
THEY BUSTED HIM BACK DOWN
TO EXORCIST FIRST CLASS.
I DON'T KNOW ALL THE DETAILS.
I HEARD SOMETHING
ABOUT HUMAN RESOURCES
AND THE VATICAN... STUFF.
[ YAWNING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ SHOUTS ]
HUH? HUH?
[ SIGHS ]
[ METALLIC CLANG ]
[ RIN ]
SO WHERE ARE WE GOING?
[ YUKIO ]
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA.
NICE. YOU WANT ME
TO GO WITH YOU,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE.
LOOK, THE DIRECTOR
HANDED ME THIS KEY,
THEN HE SAID
WE HAD TO GO TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
OH, I GET IT.
WHAT? WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU GET?
RIGHT BEFORE SATAN
POSSESSED ME,
I COULD SEE
ALL HIS MEMORIES
LIKE THEY WERE MINE.
HMM?
IT WAS HERE.
THIS IS THE FOREST
WHERE OUR MOTHER GAVE BIRTH
TO YOU AND ME.
WHERE SHE GAVE
HER LIFE FOR US.
WHOA! WHAT THE HECK?
[ YUKIO ]
SNOWMEN.
A SUBSPECIES OF GOLEMS.
MM.
LET'S GO.
THEY'RE SHOWING US THE WAY.
THAT'S IT.
WE WERE BORN
IN THAT CAVE.
HUH?
ON A SNOWY NIGHT,
OUR DAD FOUND US IN THERE.
MOM LEFT US IN HIS CARE AND--
AND THEN SHE DIED.
IS THAT... OUR MOM?
SO, UH, YOU COULD SEE HER
IN THOSE MEMORIES, RIGHT?
'CAUSE IF YOU DID SEE HER,
THEN WHAT DID SHE LOOK LIKE?
SHE WAS REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
[ GROANING ]
THAT'S ALL YOU GOT?
WHAT ABOUT, LIKE,
I DON'T KNOW.
WERE HER EYES
DOUBLE LIDDED?
RIN.
HMM?
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT...
MAYBE IT WASN'T RIGHT
THAT YOU AND I WERE BORN?
IF WE DIDN'T EXIST,
THEN MOM AND DAD WOULD STILL
BE ALIVE RIGHT NOW.
AND ALL OUR FRIENDS--
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN HURT.
YOU'RE SUCH A DORK.
[ GASPS ]
SERIOUSLY? WHAT ABOUT
EVERYTHING THEY BELIEVED?
WHAT ABOUT WHAT THEY STOOD FOR?
IT'S CAUSE OF WHO THEY WERE
THAT WE'RE EVEN HERE.
THEY MADE US WHO WE ARE.
THEY GAVE US OUR LIVES.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OUR PARENTS WERE
PRETTY AMAZING,
WEREN'T THEY?
DAMN RIGHT THEY WERE.
[ RIN ]
THEY'RE OUR PARENTS AFTER ALL.
[ MAN #1 ]
WE SEALED OFF TRUE CROSS
JUNCTION AT ROUTE 3.
[ MAN #2 ]
THE SOUTH GATE'S
ON LOCKDOWN AS WELL.
THE ENEMY IS A GHOST-RIDER,
A DEMON THAT POSSESSES CORPSES
AND CAUSES TRAFFIC ACCIDENTS,
SO STAY SHARP, PEOPLE.
HERE IT COMES.
[ ALL ]
HUH?
- WHAT UP?
- [ ALL GASPING ]
WHAT THE--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
EXWIRES ARE NOT CLEARED
FOR THESE KINDS OF MISSIONS.
AW, DON'T BE SUCH A WUSS.
BROTHERS HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER
AND BACK EACH OTHER UP NO MATTER
WHAT THE RULE BOOK SAYS.
[ YUKIO ]
WOULD YOU GET OUTTA HERE?
THIS IS DANGEROUS.
[ KURO ]
WATCH IT, RIN!
[ REVVING ENGINE ]
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
LOOK OUT!
[ SHOUTING ]
YOU DID IT!
COURSE I DID.
LOOK, RIN.
- [ TRUCK HORN BLARES ]
- [ GASPING ]
OKAY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
THAT IS A TYPE OF DEMON
THAT POSSESSES VEHICLES.
IT JUMPED FROM THE BIKE
TO THAT TRUCK.
CUT IT OUT, YUKIO!
WHY DID YOU GET
IN MY WAY?
CAN'T YOU SEE?
THERE'S SOMEONE INSIDE.
[ GROANS ]
THAT'S A HEADLESS CORPSE,
YOU IDIOT.
WE HAVE TO DESTROY IT
ALONG WITH THE SEMI.
AND WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT
TO MAKE THAT CALL?
IT'S FREAKING OUT
'CAUSE IT DIDN'T GET A FUNERAL.
BUT IF IT'S HURTING HUMANS,
WE HAVE TO DESTROY IT.
YOU'RE WRONG. AN EXORCIST'S JOB
IS TO FIGURE OUT WHAT IT WANTS,
THEN EXORCISE IT.
HELL, THAT'S WHAT
THE OLD MAN WOULD SAY.
OH, RIN.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
WOULD YOU GUYS
CUT THE CRAP ALREADY?
IT'S COMING.
[ REVVING GROWLS ]
I'LL GET
THAT THING'S ATTENTION.
WHILE I'M KEEPING IT BUSY,
YOU GUYS FIND ITS WEAK SPOT.
COME ON!
NO, WAIT!
[ SHURA ]
HEY!
[ SHOUTING ]