[ BIRDS TWITTERING ]
[ GIRL ]
THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA?
[ ELDERLY WOMAN ]
YES, SHIEMI.
HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT IT?
UH-UH. I DON'T LIKE
GOING OTHER PLACES.
THEY SAY
IT'S GOD'S GARDEN,
THE PLACE WHERE HE'S GATHERED
ALL THE PLANTS IN THE WORLD.
AND IF YOU GO THERE,
YOU CAN SEE EVERY SINGLE PLANT
UNDER THE SUN.
ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL?
REALLY?
OH, I WANNA GO THERE.
LET'S GO TOGETHER, GRANDMA.
OH, I'D LIKE TO,
BUT I'M OLD NOW
AND MY LEGS HURT.
BESIDES, THIS GARDEN
IS MY TREASURE,
AND I COULD
NEVER LEAVE IT BEHIND.
THAT WOULDN'T DO.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE
ALL GROWN UP, SHIEMI,
MAYBE YOU COULD
GO LOOK FOR IT.
MM-HMM.
♪ [ MAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ CRYING ]
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S SO... SAD.
- RIN.
- HEY! GIVE IT BACK,
DAMN IT!
I DON'T WANT YOU SOAKING
MY MANGA WITH YOUR WEIRD FLUIDS.
YOU SHOULD BE STUDYING.
HAVE YOU EVEN LOOKED...
AT ANY OF THE MATERIALS
I GAVE YOU YESTERDAY?
I LOOKED AT 'EM.
OH, I LOOKED AT 'EM,
ALL RIGHT.
BUT WHAT'S WITH THIS
"FOR KIDS" CRAP?
DO YOU THINK I'M SOME KIND
OF MORON OR SOMETHING?
NO, YOU'RE NOT A MORON.
IDIOT, YES.
MORON, NO.
[ GROWLS ]
MOLE-INFESTED, FOUR-EYED--
I SIMPLY THOUGHT
THAT IF YOU STARTED WITH THOSE,
THEY MIGHT BE A LITTLE EASIER
FOR YOU TO HANDLE.
THAT'S ANOTHER THING.
DO YOU THINK
I'M THE TYPE OF GUY...
WHO CAN SIT AT A DESK
AND FREAKING STUDY ALL DAY?
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
NOT YOU.
THE THING IS, DO YOU WANT
TO BE AN EXORCIST?
UH, WELL, YEAH.
THEN HIT THE BOOKS
AND DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF YOUR DAYS OFF.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I GOT CALLED.
ALSO, I HAVE TO GET
SOME SUPPLIES.
I WON'T BE GONE LONG.
YOU GOT CALLED
FOR AN EXORCISM?
MM-HMM.
I'M COMING WITH YOU.
I CAN LEARN WAY MORE BY
WATCHING YOU THAN BY READING
ABOUT IT IN SOME OLD BOOK.
BUT YOU'RE STILL
JUST A PAGE, RIN.
I'M SORRY, BUT THEY DON'T ALLOW
TRAINEES OUT IN THE FIELD.
[ GROANS ]
DON'T GIVE ME THAT.
WHAT THE HELL DO THEY KNOW
ABOUT ANYTHING ANYWAY?
I'M ALREADY
FIELD TESTED.
YOU HAVE A POINT.
OKAY, BUT ONLY TO WATCH.
KNEW YOU'D SEE IT MY WAY.
DO WHAT I TELL YOU,
AND DON'T ANYTHING-- ANYTHING--
WITHOUT CHECKING WITH ME FIRST.
I GOT IT, YUKIO,
LOUD AND CLEAR.
THIS IS THE KEY
TO THE SUPPLY SHOP.
IT'S ONE OF THE MANY KEYS
THAT ARE ISSUED
ONLY TO QUALIFIED EXORCISTS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
A WHOLE BOATLOAD OF 'EM.
[ GASPS ]
WHOA.
[ RIN ]
WHOA! THIS IS WAY HIGH!
WHAT'S THE POINT OF HAVING KEYS
THAT ACT LIKE WARP ZONES?
THE ACADEMY HAPPENS TO BE
AN IMPORTANT BASE
OF OPERATIONS...
FOR THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
THE DIRECTOR'S POWER PROTECTS IT
FROM PRETTY MUCH ANY ATTACK
BY MID-LEVEL DEMONS.
HE DOES IT USING A SERIES
OF TALISMANS, BARRIERS
AND EVEN LABYRINTHS.
REALLY? I GUESS HE'S NOT
YOUR AVERAGE WHACKED-OUT CLOWN
AFTER ALL.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE
THE RIGHT KEY,
YOU CAN GO ANYWHERE YOU WANT
IN THE SCHOOL WITHOUT GETTING
CAUGHT IN ONE OF HIS TRAPS.
THAT SOUNDS CONVENIENT.
[ YUKIO ]
KEYS ARE VERY IMPORTANT HERE.
IF YOU GET ONE,
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T LOSE IT.
OKAY. YOU HAVE TO WAIT HERE
WHILE I GO GET THE SUPPLIES.
- I WANNA GO TOO.
- NO. THE STORE'S FOR EXORCISTS
AND HIGHER-UPS ONLY.
- I WON'T BE LONG.
- [ GROWLS ]
- DON'T GO ANYWHERE,
AND DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING.
- YEAH, I GOT IT!
[ GROWLS ]
GEEZ, NOW THAT HE'S
MR. BIG MAN ON CAMPUS,
HE'S TREATING ME
LIKE A LITTLE KID.
"DON'T GO ANYWHERE,
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING."
WHO DOES HE THINK HE IS,
MY MOM?
JERK. ONE OF THESE DAYS,
HE'S GONNA BE THE ONE
THAT'S COUNTING ON ME.
HUH?
[ BIRDS TWITTERING ]
[ WATER TRICKLING ]
NO WAY!
IT'S AWESOME IN THERE.
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
- [ GASPS ]
- [ EXPLOSION ]
[ CREAKING ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
UH, I DIDN'T DO IT.
IT JUST HAPPENED.
HUH? DEMON!
HUH?
- THAT GATE
HAS A SPELL ON IT.
- IT DOES?
OH, CRAP. IT REACTED TO ME.
[ WHIMPERS ]
G-GO AWAY, YOU DEMON.
[ GROWLS ]
WATCH WHO YOU'RE CALLING
A DEMON!
DON'T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS.
I'M NOT A DEMON, GOT IT?
[ WHIMPERS, SCREAMS ]
STAY AWAY!
- UH, HEY.
- DON'T COME NEAR ME!
UM, IS SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR LEGS?
HUH?
[ YUKIO ]
VALERIANA, HYPERICUM,
FERN, HOREHOUND.
TWO OF EACH, PLEASE.
UH, ONE LITER
OF C-DENSITY HOLY WATER
AND 300 GRAMS OF IRON SAND.
OH, AND SIX DOZEN
OF THE USUAL
HOLY SILVER BULLETS.
STOCKPILING AGAIN?
YOU ARE A GOOD CUSTOMER.
I BURNED THROUGH
MOST OF OUR SUPPLIES
THE OTHER DAY.
SO ANYWAY,
ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER--
HOW IS SHIEMI DOING?
NOT TOO GOOD.
HER LEGS ARE GETTING WORSE
EVERY DAY.
EVERY SINGLE DOCTOR
I'VE TAKEN HER TO
CAN'T FIND ANYTHING WRONG.
THEY ALL SAY SHE'S FINE.
THAT'S WHY I ASKED YOU TO COME.
WHAT DOES SHIEMI
HAVE TO SAY?
WELL, YOU MIGHT SAY WE HAD
A BIT OF A FALLING OUT.
WE'RE NOT SPEAKING MUCH
THESE DAYS.
HAS ANYTHING HAPPENED TO HER
THAT COULD BE DEMON RELATED?
MM.
MY MOTHER--
SHIEMI'S GRANDMOTHER--
PASSED AWAY LAST WINTER.
WHOA. THAT'S RANK.
MY EYES ARE STINGING.
I MIX COW DUNG AND WATER
TO MAKE THE FERTILIZER.
COW DUNG, HUH?
THANK GOODNESS
I HAD YOU AROUND.
I NEEDED THE HOLE DUG
REALLY DEEP.
THANK GOODNESS,
MY ASS.
FIRST YOU CALL ME A DEMON,
AND THEN YOU START
BOSSING ME AROUND?
WELL, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I WAS JUST SCARED.
[ SIGHS ]
- HUH?
- CAN WE MAKE UP NOW?
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU,
I DIDN'T REALIZE
WHAT A GOOD PERSON YOU WERE.
[ STAMMERS ]
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO,
I DON'T MIND.
OH, I'M GLAD.
OKAY, I CAN GO FIRST.
- I'M SHIEMI MORIYAMA.
- RIN. RIN OKUMURA.
[ GASPS ]
SHE MIXED COW POO
WITH THAT HAND!
THIS IS A SPECIAL PLACE
FOR ME.
IT'S MY GRANDMA'S GARDEN.
I'D HELP HER WITH THE PLANTING,
AND SHE'D TEACH ME
ALL KINDS OF THINGS.
I-- I LOVE THIS GARDEN,
AND I LOVE MY GRANDMA.
BUT LAST WINTER,
WHILE WORKING IN THE GARDEN,
SHE HAD AN ACCIDENT AND DIED.
I THINK WHEN SHE DIED, SHE WENT
TO THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA.
I HOPE SO ANYWAY.
GARDEN OF AMAHARA?
GRANDMA SAID
IT'S A PLACE GOD CREATED...
WHERE HE GATHERED
ALL THE PLANTS
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
I KNOW IT'S JUST A FAIRY TALE,
BUT IF THERE REALLY IS
A GARDEN OF AMAHARA,
A SPECIAL PLACE WHERE I CAN GO
AND WANDER AROUND...
LOOKING AT ALL THE PLANTS
IN THE WORLD,
THEN I'D LIKE TO GO THERE.
[ YUKIO ]
RIN!
- OH.
- HUH?
I CAN'T LET YOU
OUT OF MY SIGHT
FOR A SECOND.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- HE-HEY, YUKIO.
YUKI!
"YUKI"?
- YOU KNOW HER?
- YES.
SHIEMI'S MOTHER RUNS THE SHOP.
I SEE HER
EVERY TIME I COME HERE.
HOW ARE YOU DOING, SHIEMI?
HE-HELLO, YUKI.
WE'RE TWINS.
HE'S THE OLDER ONE.
[ GASPS ]
BUT YOU SEEM MORE LIKE
HIS BIG BROTHER.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I AM MORE MATURE THAN HE IS.
TECHNICALLY, THOUGH,
HE IS THE OLDER ONE.
TECHNICALLY?
WHATEVER!
SHIEMI, COME ON.
LET HIM HAVE A LOOK
AT YOUR LEGS.
BUT, MOM, I TOLD YOU
I HAVEN'T BEEN INFECTED.
IT'S JUST A PRECAUTION.
IF I DON'T FIND ANYTHING,
YOU'RE NONE THE WORSE OFF,
RIGHT?
WILL YOU LET ME TAKE A LOOK?
MM-HMM.
IT'S OKAY.
- A ROOT.
- [ RIN ] HUH?
IT'S A TEMPTAINT.
A DEMON CAUSED THIS.
- BUT THAT CAN'T BE.
- SHE'S NOT POSSESSED,
IS SHE?
NO. SHE'S DEFINITELY
NOT POSSESSED.
THE DEMON THAT DID THIS
ISN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO POSSESS A HUMAN.
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE WORK
OF A DOÖKKÁLFAR--
A GREEN MAN...
OR AN ENT.
THEY'RE LOW-LEVEL DEMONS
THAT POSSESS GRASS AND TREES.
ONE OF THEM REACHED THROUGH
THE SOIL INTO SHIEMI'S LEGS
AND IS FEEDING OFF HER SOUL.
THE DEMON IS SOMEWHERE
IN THIS GARDEN.
[ WHIMPERS ]
SHIEMI, USUALLY A DEMON
CAN FIND ITS WAY...
INTO A PERSON'S SOUL
THROUGH CONVERSATION.
YOU MUST HAVE SPOKEN
WITH ONE.
[ WHIMPERS ]
CAN YOU REMEMBER
DOING THAT?
NO. I DIDN'T.
I NEVER SPOKE WITH ANY DEMON.
SHIEMI! WE HAVE TO GET YOU
OUT OF THIS GARDEN NOW!
I KNOW YOUR GRANDMOTHER
LOVED IT, BUT THIS HAS GONE
FAR ENOUGH, YOUNG LADY.
I WON'T LET YOU RISK YOUR HEALTH
OVER THIS CURSED PLACE.
THIS GARDEN ISN'T CURSED.
THIS PLACE WAS GRANDMA'S
GREATEST TREASURE.
I WON'T LEAVE IT, MOM!
I HATE YOU!
[ GASPS ]
OH, SHIEMI!
SHIEMI!
[ GRANDMOTHER ]
GOOD, SHIEMI.
NOW HERE'S ANOTHER TIP.
YOU PLANT ROOT VEGETABLES
WHEN THE MOON WAXES,
AND LEAFY PLANTS
WHEN THE MOON WANES.
- GOT IT.
- YOU REALLY LOVE
PLANTS AND FLOWERS,
- DON'T YOU, SHIEMI?
- MM-HMM.
AND I LOVE YOU TOO.
DON'T FORGET.
I'LL STAY WITH YOU FOREVER.
WITH YOU... FOREVER.
EVEN THOUGH SHE LOOKS FINE
ON THE OUTSIDE,
THE DEMON IS DRAINING
HER ENERGY
THROUGH HER LEGS.
IF IT ISN'T EXORCISED SOON,
SHE WILL DIE.
[ YUKIO ]
WHY IS SHE SLEEPING OUT
HERE IN THE STOREHOUSE?
[ MOTHER ]
OH, WELL, THIS IS WHERE
HER GRANDMOTHER LIVED.
AFTER HER GRANDMOTHER DIED,
SHE DECIDED SHE WASN'T GOING
TO LEAVE THE GARDEN AGAIN,
AND THEN SHE MOVED IN.
THAT'S ABOUT THE TIME
SHE STARTED HAVING TROUBLE
WITH HER LEGS.
JUST LIKE HER GRANDMOTHER.
HER LEGS BOTHERED HER TOO.
THE MEMORIES OF HER GRANDMOTHER
MUST WEIGH HEAVILY ON HER MIND.
FORGIVE ME FOR PRYING,
BUT IS THAT THE REASON...
YOU AND SHIEMI HAVEN'T
BEEN GETTING ALONG?
YES,
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD SAY THAT.
I WASN'T REALLY CUT OUT
FOR MOTHERHOOD.
AND I WASN'T A GOOD DAUGHTER
EITHER, I'M AFRAID.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN A FRAIL CHILD,
AND WHEN SHE WAS A LITTLE GIRL,
SHE'D GET SICK
WHENEVER SHE WENT TO SCHOOL.
BUT SINCE I WAS ALWAYS
SO BUSY WITH THE SHOP,
HER GRANDMOTHER WAS THE ONE
WHO TOOK CARE OF HER.
I COULDN'T HELP FEELING
A LITTLE JEALOUS.
SHE AND HER GRANDMOTHER
WERE SO CLOSE,
AND I FELT LEFT OUT.
IN THE END, IT'S MY FAULT
WE BECAME SO DISTANT
FROM EACH OTHER.
AND HERE I AM,
ACTING ALL CONCERNED,
LIKE THE KIND OF MOTHER
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
ALL ALONG.
YOU'RE NOT HELPING HER
BY THINKING THAT WAY.
IN FACT, YOU'RE PLAYING
RIGHT INTO THE DEMON'S HANDS.
THEY EXPLOIT THE WEAKNESSES
OF A PERSON'S SOUL.
[ GIGGLES ]
[ GRANDMOTHER ]
SHIEMI! SHIEMI,
GIVE ME A HAND, WILL YOU?
THE FROST IS COMING,
AND WE HAVE TO COVER...
THE GRAPE ARBOR
BEFORE IT GETS HERE.
BUT, GRANDMA, I'M GOING TO LOOK
FOR THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA.
REALLY?
I SAVED A BUNCH OF MONEY
FOR THE TRIP, YOU SEE?
I MIGHT EVEN HAVE ENOUGH
TO TRAVEL ALL OVER THE WORLD.
YOU'RE LEAVING THE GARDEN?
[ GIGGLES ]
GO HAVE FUN THEN.
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE
ENOUGH IN THAT PURSE TO MAKE IT
ALL THE WAY AROUND THE WORLD.
OH. I DON'T?
BUT MAYBE TODAY
YOU COULD LOOK FOR IT
NEARBY.
OKAY. I'LL COVER THE GRAPE ARBOR
AS SOON AS I GET BACK, GRANDMA.
OH, DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT THAT.
BE CAREFUL NOW.
AND MAKE SURE YOU COME HOME
BEFORE IT GETS DARK, OKAY?
[ SNIFFLING ]
GRANDMA? THE PANSIES
HAVEN'T SPROUTED YET.
AND HOW AM I GONNA FIX
THE GRAPE ARBOR?
IF I DON'T DO SOMETHING,
YOUR GARDEN WILL DIE.
[ WEEPING ]
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
[ FEMALE VOICE ]
YOU SHOULD PROTECT THE GARDEN.
WHO'S THAT?
I CAN HELP YOU PROTECT IT...
IF YOU WANT.
[ GASPS ]
WAS THAT YOU TALKING
A SECOND AGO?
YES. I'M A FAIRY.
I LIVE HERE.
WILL YOU HELP ME PROTECT
THIS GARDEN?
I WILL! I'LL HELP YOU.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN.
JUST PLEASE KEEP
GRANDMA'S GARDEN SAFE.
SHE LOVED IT
SO MUCH.
THEN LET'S PROTECT
THIS GARDEN TOGETHER. FOREVER.
PROMISE ME.
I HAVEN'T DONE THE WATERING
THIS EVENING.
I HAVE TO GO.
I HAVE TO PROTECT IT.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ RIN ]
HEY, DOING SOME
LATE-NIGHT GARDENING?
YOU KNOW, YOUR MOM'S
REALLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I DON'T CARE.
WHAT DOES SHE KNOW
ABOUT ANYTHING?
THIS IS WHAT I WANT.
I DON'T CARE WHAT ANYONE SAYS!
I'LL PROTECT GRANDMA'S GARDEN!
HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP IT!
NO, STOP!
[ SHATTERING ]
PLEASE, JUST STOP.
WOULD YOU SNAP OUT
OF IT ALREADY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS
TO YOURSELF?
IF I--
IF ONLY I'D COME HOME
EARLIER THAT DAY THEN--
I'M BACK, GRANDMA.
SORRY I'M SO LATE.
[ GASPS ]
GRANDMA?
GRANDMA!
IF I'D STAYED AND HELPED HER
WITH THE ARBOR,
GRANDMA WOULDN'T HAVE DIED.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
SHE DIED BECAUSE OF ME.
THAT'S WHY--
THAT'S WHY NO MATTER WHAT,
I HAVE TO PROTECT HER GARDEN.
NO WAY.
SHE'S JUST LIKE ME.
TRAPPED IN THE PAST,
BLAMING HERSELF.
[ SOBS ]
THEN STOP MAKING
YOUR MOM WORRY ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
WHAT YOU'RE DOING
ISN'T WORTH IT.
COME ON, WHAT HAPPENED
TO GETTING OUT IN THE WORLD...
AND FINDING
THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA?
- YOU FORGET ABOUT THAT?
- [ GASPS ]
WHAT WOULD YOUR GRANDMA SAY?
WOULD SHE TELL YOU NOT TO GO?
IS THAT WHAT SHE'D SAY?
GO HAVE FUN THEN.
[ CRYING ]
UH-UH.
SHE WOULDN'T.
SHE WOULDN'T SAY THAT.
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
I CAN'T MOVE MY LEGS ANYMORE.
I GOT THIS.
I'M GONNA CHOP THE HELL
OUT OF THAT DAMN ROOT.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT YOU.
IT WAS JUST GETTING GOOD.
HUH?
[ SHOUTS ]
WHEN'D YOU GET HERE?
THIS DEMON IS A LIGHTWEIGHT.
I CAN EXORCISE IT IN NO TIME.
DON'T WORRY, SHIEMI.
YOUR LEGS ARE GOING
TO WORK AGAIN.
IT'S UP TO YOU THOUGH.
YOU HAVE TO WANT THIS.
I DO.
[ DEMON ]
I WON'T ALLOW IT.
YOU'RE BREAKING YOUR PROMISE.
IT'S REVEALED ITSELF.
I WON'T LET YOU.
[ SHIEMI SCREAMS ]
SHIEMI!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WE'RE GOING TO BE
TOGETHER FOREVER.
YOU'LL LIVE IN THIS GARDEN
TILL THE DAY YOU DIE.
DAMN IT, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE BLOOMING THIS LATE
AT NIGHT.
[ YUKIO ]
OH, NO, IT'S USING HER
AS A SHIELD.
HEY, RIN.
YEAH?
I THINK I'M GOING TO NEED
YOUR HELP WITH THIS THING.
HUH?
YOU UP FOR IT?
SORRY, COULD YOU SAY THAT AGAIN?
I SAID I NEED YOUR HELP!
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL, SINCE YOU'RE
MY LITTLE BROTHER AND ALL,
YOU DON'T NEED TO TWIST MY ARM.
I'D LOVE TO GIVE YOU A HAND.
[ SNARLS ]
[ GASPS ]
YOU'RE A DEMON LIKE ME.
YOU GOT THE WRONG IDEA, STINKY.
I'M NOTHING LIKE YOU!
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU LOSE YOUR CONFIDENCE?
QUIT PLAYING DIRTY, YOU.
WHEN IT COMES TO DEMONS,
THERE'S NO PLAYING CLEAN.
STRIKE ME WITH YOUR SWORD,
I DARE YOU.
I HOPE YOU WON'T REGRET
ALL THE BIG RED GASHES...
YOU'RE GOING TO PUT
ON OUR PRETTY BODIES.
GET BACK, RIN.
AT THIS POINT,
I HAVE TO SHOOT THEM BOTH.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
HA! YOU'RE BLUFFING.
YOU WOULDN'T
SACRIFICE THE GIRL.
YOU CAN'T FOOL ME.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
[ GASPS ]
YOU COULD BE RIGHT...
OR YOU COULD BE DEAD WRONG.
YUKIO.
I WONDER WHICH ONE
IT'S GOING TO BE.
DAMN YOU, EXORCIST!
YOU WOULDN'T DARE SHOOT US.
NO!
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE, RIN!
- [ RIN SHOUTING ]
- NO!
SON OF A--
- YUKI.
- [ RIN ]
HUH?
YOU'RE OKAY.
THE ROOT ON YOUR LEGS
IS GONE.
TRY STANDING.
HUH?
YOU'RE OKAY.
[ GASPS ]
[ MOTHER ]
SHIEMI!
HI, MOM.
GET OVER THERE.
[ BOTH GASP ]
RIN--
MAN, JUST TELL HER
YOU'RE SORRY.
IF YOU DON'T TELL HER NOW,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA REGRET IT.
UM--
YOU KNOW,
THERE ONCE WAS A TIME...
WHEN EVEN I TRIED
TO FIND THAT PLACE--
THE GARDEN OF AMAHARA.
[ GASPS ]
YOU SILLY GIRL,
MAKING ME WORRY SO MUCH.
OH, MOM, I'M SORRY.
[ BOTH CRYING ]
IT'S COOL
WHEN THINGS WORK OUT LIKE THIS.
HEY, WHAT KIND OF BULLET
DID YOU SHOOT HER WITH ANYWAY?
PLANT VITAMINS.
IT STINGS FOR A LITTLE BIT,
BUT THAT'S ALL.
AH, ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT'S IT?
WE SAVED HER, BUT SOMEHOW
IT FEELS LIKE I WAS THE ONE
WHO GOT SAVED.
♪ [ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
OH.
SO THIS IS YOUR NEW CLASSMATE,
SHIEMI MORIYAMA.
I-IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU ALL.
UH, WHAT THE--
I DECIDED TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE WORLD...
AND I WANT TO BE STRONGER.
SO I ASKED YUKI--
I MEAN, MR. OKUMURA--
TO GET ME IN.
YOU'RE SUPER TENSE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M SURPRISED
YOU EVEN MADE IT HERE.
YOU'RE THE REASON FOR THAT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, RIN.
HUH? UH, NAH, IT'S COOL.
ALSO I WANTED TO SEE
WHAT YUKI WAS LIKE
AS A TEACHER.
[ SIGHING ]
UH, YEAH,
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
HMM.
IT'S 'CAUSE YOU KEEP FLIRTING
WITH THAT GIRL, JACKASS.
[ RIN ] I'M THE ONE
WHO'S GONNA DEFEAT SATAN,
SO STAY OUTTA MY WAY!
[ MEPHISTO ]
BESIDES, THE FUN
IS JUST BEGINNING.