YOU AGAIN.
RIN OKUMURA--
SON OF SATAN.
[ GASPS ]
YUKIO.
THAT GUY.
HE'S OUR--
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
MEPHISTO?
WHOOPSY DAISY.
HOLA, MY YOUNG PAGES.
MANY THANKS
FOR ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
IT'S THE DIRECTOR.
WHA-WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU DIDN'T THINK I'D LET
AN UPPER-LEVEL DEMON JUST WALTZ
ONTO MY CAMPUS, DID YOU?
[ RIN ]
HUH?
INSTRUCTORS
WITH DOCTOR CREDENTIALS,
TEND TO THE WOUNDED.
YOU GUYS WERE--
SURPRISE! THIS WAS
NO ORDINARY BOOT CAMP, KIDS.
IN FACT, YOU'VE JUST COMPLETED
YOUR EXWIRE AUTHORIZATION EXAM.
UH--
IT'S RATHER SNEAKY,
I KNOW.
THIS WHOLE TIME WE HAD
A TEAM OF INSTRUCTORS HIDDEN
THROUGHOUT THE BUILDING...
IN PLACES WHERE THEY COULD
OBSERVE YOUR EVERY MOVE.
AFTER I HAVE A CHANCE
TO REVIEW THEIR REPORTS,
I'LL BE THE ONE TO DETERMINE
WHO PASSED AND WHO FAILED.
I'M SURE YOU'RE AS ANXIOUS
AS I AM TO SEE HOW YOU DID.
♪ [ MAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
DAMN IT!
MAN, THAT WAS
THE WORST POP QUIZ EVER.
[ SUGURO ]
THEY TRICKED US
PRETTY GOOD.
I WISH I WOULD'VE KNOWN
BECAUSE I COULD'VE
PREPARED FOR IT.
OH, BOY.
I WONDER
IF I PASSED.
DON'T TORTURE YOURSELF.
THERE'S NO USE WORRYING
ABOUT IT NOW.
YOU AND SHIMA
DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
BUT ME--
I WAS SO SCARED
I COULDN'T MOVE MY LEGS.
I'M SURE YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO BE FINE.
REMEMBER WHAT MR. OKUMURA
TOLD US
BEFORE THE TEST STARTED?
EXORCISTS DO NOT GO
INTO BATTLE ALONE.
SO COOL OFF AND GET ALONG
UNTIL I GET BACK.
BEING AN EXWIRE
TAKES COOPERATION.
THEY HAVE TO WORK
WITH THEIR TEAM DURING COMBAT.
IN THAT SENSE,
NO ONE DID WORSE THAN ME.
YOU NEED TO CUT YOURSELF
SOME SLACK THERE.
YOU STEPPED UP,
NOT LIKE THOSE GUYS.
THEY JUST SAT AROUND.
YOU GOT ANYTHING
TO SAY FOR YOURSELVES? HUH?
OH, SWEET.
I JUST SCORED MYSELF
A DRAGON CLAW.
HA! WHY DON'T YOU SHUT
YOUR PIE HOLE?
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY
TO A BUNCH OF WHINY BRATS
LIKE YOU.
[ GROWLING ]
WHOA, THEY TALKED!
THEY'VE BEEN MYSTERIOUS
SINCE THE FIRST DAY.
AND THAT GUY ROCKS
AT VENTRILOQUISM.
[ GROANS ]
UH, SHOOT.
I WOKE YOU UP.
MY BAD.
OH, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M FEELING BETTER NOW.
REALLY.
WHAT WERE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
OH, JUST ABOUT THE EXAM
AND STUFF.
AND ABOUT HOW AWESOME YOU WERE.
YOU OUTDID US ALL.
IF YOU WEREN'T THERE, MORIYAMA,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED TO US.
WE OWE YOU BIG-TIME.
WHAT? UH, NO.
I SHOULD BE THANKING YOU.
I KNOW YOU'LL PASS THE EXAM.
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, IF YOU DON'T PASS,
WE'RE DEFINITELY
NOT GONNA PASS.
[ GIGGLES ]
HEY, OKUMURA, HOW DID YOU KILL
THAT GHOUL ALL BY YOURSELF?
HUH?
OH, WELL, I, UH--
I SORT OF...
SHOVED THIS INTO IT.
WHOA, THAT'S AMAZING.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY
TO BE A KNIGHT.
OKAY. WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
SHOVED INTO IT?
COULD YOU BE ANY MORE VAGUE?
IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU'RE THE MYSTERIOUS ONE.
UH-HUH. IT'S LIKE
I DON'T LOOK IT,
BUT I GOT THIS CERTAIN
"MISTAKE" ABOUT ME.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU JUST SAID "MISTAKE."
OH, I MEANT "MISKEE."
"MISKOO."
IT'S "MYSTIQUE,"
YOU DUMBASS.
HE'S A PAGE, BUT HE BEAT
A MID-LEVEL DEMON
WITHOUT ANY BACKUP.
WITH ONLY A SWORD?
NO WAY.
HE REALLY IS A MYSTERY.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ YUKIO ]
MR. NOIHAUS.
I'D LIKE TO HAVE A WORD
WITH YOU.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S ABOUT YESTERDAY.
YOUR ACTIONS OVERSTEPPED
THE BOUNDARIES OF THE EXAM.
WHAT WERE YOU TRYING
TO ACCOMPLISH?
EVEN IF IT WAS
FOR EVALUATION PURPOSES,
YOU EXPOSED THE STUDENTS
TO UNNECESSARY DANGER.
THE EXAM COULD'VE TURNED
INTO A DISASTER.
ALSO, YOU ALMOST FORCED
MY BROTHER TO REVEAL HIS POWER
IN FRONT OF THE OTHER STUDENTS.
ONLY A HANDFUL OF INSTRUCTORS
HERE KNOW THE TRUTH
ABOUT RIN'S CAPABILITIES.
SIR PHELES MUST HAVE SWORN YOU
TO SECRECY LIKE HE DID
THE REST OF US.
YOUR CONCERNS ARE NOTED.
HOWEVER, I WAS ACTING
ON SIR PHELES' ORDERS.
[ GASPS ]
HE TOLD ME
TO TRY TO KILL HIM.
HE SAID THAT?
MY UNDERSTANDING
OF THE SITUATION IS...
THAT YOU ARE TO SERVE
AS THE BRAKES TO HIS POWER.
IF THAT IS SO,
THEN I AM TO SERVE
AS THE ACCELERATOR.
AND THE PURPOSE OF IT ALL
IS TO GAIN AN ACCURATE READING
OF RIN OKUMURA'S CAPABILITIES.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT, MY YOUNG COLLEAGUE,
SHOULD BE OBVIOUS.
WE'RE TRYING TO FIND OUT
WHETHER OR NOT WE CAN USE HIM
AS A WEAPON FOR THE ORDER.
YOU MUST BE
VERY BUSY THESE DAYS,
BEING A BRILLIANT EXORCIST
AND ALL.
THE LEAST WE COULD DO IS HELP
WITH THE CHORE OF BABY-SITTING
YOUR DEMON BROTHER.
MY BROTHER CAN CONTROL
HIS EMOTIONS AND HIS POWER
JUST FINE.
FOR THE TIME BEING.
YOU'VE SEEN IT
WITH YOUR OWN EYES.
BUT DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE
HIS ABILITIES.
COME NOW.
I'M NOT REALLY
GOING TO KILL YOUR BROTHER.
YOU HAVE MY WORD ON THAT.
[ FROGS CROAKING ]
WE HAD A BUSY DAY YESTERDAY,
DIDN'T WE, NEE?
NEE!
NEE-EE!
- THANK YOU.
- BUT YOU DID SAVE US TODAY.
WE REALLY OWE YOU BIG-TIME.
NEE!
[ GASPS ]
WELCOME TO THE STORE.
HI, SHIEMI.
HOW ARE YOU?
[ GASPS ]
YUKI!
SORRY TO COME HERE
SO LATE.
IS YOUR MOM IN?
SHE WENT TO GET MORE SUPPLIES,
SO I'M WATCHING THE STORE.
CAN I HELP YOU
WITH ANYTHING?
[ SHRIEKING ]
WE'RE ALONE!
ACTUALLY, I CAME TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT YOUR FUTURE PLANS.
ARE YOU FREE,
OR SHOULD I COME BACK?
WELL, I'M IN
A WEIRD SPOT...
BECAUSE I'M NOT GOING
TO CRAM SCHOOL TO BE AN EXORCIST
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE,
SO I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT MEISTER TO WRITE DOWN.
I WISH I WASN'T
SO UNSURE ABOUT THINGS.
UH, SHIEMI, DO YOU REMEMBER
THE DAY WE FIRST MET...
- WHEN I CAME HERE
WITH MY FATHER?
- HUH?
I HAD JUST BECOME AN EXORCIST,
AND I REMEMBER IT
LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
I WAS SO NERVOUS AND TENSE.
[ GASPS ]
LOOSEN UP.
YOU'RE GONNA BLOW A FUSE
IF YOU'RE WOUND UP LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST A SUPPLY SHOP.
RIGHT!
WHAT'S SHAKIN', MA'AM?
THIS IS MY SON, YUKIO.
AND AS OF TODAY,
HE'S AN EXORCIST.
THING IS,
KID'S NOT EVEN 14 YET,
SO IF I'M NOT AROUND,
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU,
MA'AM.
WELL, WELL, WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
MY, YOU LOOK LIKE
SUCH A FINE YOUNG MAN.
OH, WAIT.
WHERE IS SHIEMI?
SHIEMI, CAN YOU COME OUT
FOR A SECOND?
HMM?
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
SHE'S LIKE A LITTLE GHOST,
ISN'T SHE?
[ LAUGHS ]
SHE'S AS SHY
AS A MOUSE--
NOTHING LIKE HER MOTHER,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
COME ON OUT.
THIS YOUNG MAN IS
THE SAME AGE AS YOU,
AND GUESS WHAT?
HE'S AN EXORCIST TEACHER.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS YUKIO OKUMURA.
HELLO.
AH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
POOR THING'S AS SHY
AS SHE EVER WAS.
I THOUGHT AT THE VERY LEAST
SHE'D STICK AROUND AND GET
TO KNOW SOMEONE HER OWN AGE.
DON'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
[ SHIEMI ]
TEACHER!
WELL, NOW.
TEACHER.
HMM.
OH. WHO, ME?
HERE'S A CHARM...
FOR YOU.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL AT WORK.
OH.
THANK YOU.
TEACHER.
UH, LISTEN, UM,
CALLING ME TEACHER'S
SO FORMAL.
COULD YOU CALL ME SOMETHING
MORE CASUAL INSTEAD?
[ SHRIEKS ]
OKAY.
YOU COULD CALL ME--
I'LL CALL YOU YUKI.
- HUH?
- HOW ABOUT
IF I CALL YOU YUKI?
OH. WELL, I--
IT'S CUTE.
I GUESS THAT'LL WORK.
- SURE. WHY NOT?
- [ SIGHS ]
I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
I'M SORRY.
I WAS EVEN WEIRDER BACK THEN
THAN I AM NOW.
IT'S JUST-- THERE YOU WERE,
THIS AMAZING PERSON,
AND I REALLY LOOKED UP TO YOU.
WELL, AMAZING MIGHT BE GOING
A BIT TOO FAR.
- HUH?
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I WAS A CRYBABY.
MY BROTHER WAS ALWAYS THE ONE
WHO GOT ME OUT OF TROUBLE.
NO WAY.
REALLY? YOU?
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE WAS ALWAYS ABLE TO DO
THE THINGS THAT I COULDN'T.
MY BROTHER WAS EVERYTHING
I WANTED TO BE.
I LOOKED UP TO HIM.
HE'S SWEET.
I CAN SEE WHY YOU WOULD.
YOU'RE RIGHT. HE IS.
BUT AT SOME POINT,
WE ALL HAVE TO GROW UP,
DON'T WE?
YOU WORKED HARD
TO GET THIS FAR, SHIEMI.
YOU'VE CHANGED A LOT.
BUT IF YOU WANT
TO KEEP ATTENDING CLASSES
AT THE CRAM SCHOOL,
YOU HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION.
SHIEMI, EVERYONE KNOWS
YOU HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO BECOME A TAMER.
I'D LIKE FOR YOU
TO REALLY THINK ABOUT.
TALK TO YOUR MOTHER FIRST,
AND LET ME KNOW WHAT YOUR
DECISION IS BY TOMORROW.
- I HAVE TO TALK
TO MY MOM?
- YOU SHOULD.
IF YOU BECOME AN EXWIRE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO BE PREPARED
TO FACE LIFE-OR-DEATH
SITUATIONS.
WE'LL NEED HER CONSENT
FOR THAT.
YEAH, THAT FIGURES.
DURING THE EXAM I WASN'T SO SURE
I WAS EVEN GOING TO MAKE IT.
RIGHT. I KNOW
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
A GRUELING EXPERIENCE FOR YOU.
BUT IT WAS ONLY A TEST,
AFTER ALL.
WE TOOK EXTRA MEASURES,
SO YOU WEREN'T
IN ANY REAL DANGER.
AT LEAST...
THAT'S WHAT THE PLAN WAS.
ALL THE TEACHERS HAD...
YOUR SAFETY IN MIND.
I'M NOT REALLY GOING
TO KILL YOUR BROTHER.
[ GASPS ]
EXCUSE ME.
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
BUT, YUKI--
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ SNORING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ GASPS, SIGHS ]
[ GUN COCKS ]
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WEREN'T GOING
TO KILL HIM,
MR. NOIHAUS.
WELL PLAYED, YUKIO OKUMURA.
RIN?
[ YELLS ]
SHIEMI! WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY ROOM?
NOT THAT I MIND
OR ANYTHING.
SHH. WE'RE NOT IN YOUR ROOM.
YOU WOULDN'T WAKE UP,
SO YUKI BROUGHT YOU HERE.
HE SAID TO LET YOU SLEEP,
BUT I HEARD SOMETHING.
- [ TWO GUNSHOTS ]
- [ BOTH GASP ]
COME FORTH!
NOIHAUS, WHY ARE YOU TRYING
TO KILL MY BROTHER?
[ GRUNTING ]
YOU'RE SLOW.
FROM A CORPSE IN THE GROUND
WHERE VULTURES
WON'T GATHER ROUND, ARISE.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU'RE ABOUT TO MEET
THE HIGHEST RANKING NABERIUS...
AMONGST ALL MY PAWNS.
[ ROARING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
[ YUKIO ]
I HAVE TO BREAK
THE MAGIC CIRCLE.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ ROARING ]
DAMN YOU!
I KNEW IT!
- YOU CURSED DEMON!
- [ RIN SHOUTING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU LOOK HUMAN, BUT HOLY WATER
WORKS ON YOU LIKE ALL DEMONS.
YOU CAN'T HIDE YOUR NATURE,
EVEN WITH THE SKIN
YOU'RE WEARING.
HOLY WATER?
WHAT THE HELL?
[ SHOUTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT THE--
[ PANTING ]
DAMN. HE BROKE THE CIRCLE.
NOIHAUS, FOR YOUR OWN GOOD,
YOU'D BETTER STOP THIS NOW.
IF YOU LOSE ANY MORE BLOOD,
YOU'LL DIE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
WHAT AM I?
A SURVIVOR OF THE BLUE NIGHT.
THE BLUE NIGHT?
HERE'S WHAT HAPPENED.
SIXTEEN YEARS AGO SATAN CROSSED
THE BARRIER TO OUR WORLD...
AND MASSACRED
ALL THE TOP CLERGYMEN.
WE'VE CALLED IT
THE BLUE NIGHT EVER SINCE.
YOU DON'T SAY?
IT LASTED A FEW SECONDS.
MY BODY WAS POSSESSED
BY SATAN,
AND I LOST THIS.
MY EYE. THERE WAS NOTHING
I COULD DO TO STOP IT.
AND WHEN MY FAMILY
TRIED TO SAVE ME,
SATAN TOOK OVER MY HAND
AND USED IT TO SLAUGHTER
THEM ALL.
I WON'T FORGIVE SATAN...
OR ANY DEMON
I COME ACROSS.
AND THAT GOES FOR THE SON
OF SATAN AS WELL!
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU,
EVEN IF IT MEANS I DIE DOING IT!
[ GROANING ]
DID THAT MAKE YOU FEEL
ANY BETTER?
RIN!
IF YOU THINK
YOU'RE STILL NOT SATISFIED,
I CAN HANDLE MORE.
I'M USED TO IT.
PICK THE TIME,
AND I'LL BE THERE
WAITING FOR YOU.
BUT YOU GOTTA PROMISE ME...
THAT YOU WON'T DRAG
INNOCENT PEOPLE INTO IT AGAIN.
[ GASPS ]
DON'T THINK FOR A SECOND
THAT IT'S OVER.
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
THAT'D LOVE TO SEE YOU DIE.
GET READY FOR WHAT'S COMING.
[ PANTING ]
NEE?
YUKI? RIN?
MR. NOIHAUS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
IT'S ALREADY STARTING
TO CLOSE UP.
YOU KNOW ME.
I ALWAYS HEALED UP PRETTY QUICK.
I GUESS THAT MEANS
I REALLY AM A MONSTER.
[ DOOR BANGS ]
[ SHIEMI ]
YUKI! RIN!
SHIEMI.
R-RIN! WHAT HAPPENED?
[ GASPS ]
UH, NOTHING.
I'M FINE.
THAT'S A GHOUL
TEMPTAINT!
I HAVE TO TREAT IT.
NO. I'M OKAY.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
NO ARGUMENTS.
LIE DOWN
AND TRY TO STAY CALM.
HUH?
I SAID LIE DOWN!
NEE, MAY I HAVE
SOME MR. SANCHO?
NEE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S GREAT, THANKS.
YEAH, I THINK IT'S WORKING.
I FEEL WAY BETTER NOW.
RIN, I'VE DECIDED.
HUH?
I'VE DECIDED.
OKAY. WHAT'D YOU DECIDE?
RIN, YOU WERE
ALWAYS ABLE TO DO
THE THINGS I COULDN'T.
OH, WELL. GUESS
I'LL NEVER BE A MATCH FOR HIM.
EINS, ZWEI, DREI.
CONGRATULATIONS
ON PASSING THE EXAM!
YOU'VE ALL BEEN PROMOTED
TO BECOME EXWIRES.
[ CHEERING ]
ALL RIGHT!
- THANK GOODNESS.
- [ LAUGHS ]
AND TO CELEBRATE,
I'M TREATING YOU ALL TO A FEAST.
WHO'S HUNGRY FOR MONJA?
[ ALL ]
WHAT?
MONJA?
BARBECUE'S WAY BETTER.
[ RIN ]
SO YOU'RE GONNA BE
AN EXORCIST, HUH?
YEP. I'M GONNA HELP
EVERYONE OUT.
UH, YOU GONNA BE OKAY
FIGHTING?
OF COURSE I'LL BE OKAY.
REALLY?
I MUST APOLOGIZE
FOR MR. NOIHAUS'S
RECENT BEHAVIOR.
BELIEVE ME, I NEVER DREAMED
HE'D LET HIS PERSONAL FEELINGS
INTERFERE IN SUCH A WAY.
I'LL MAKE SURE SUCH A THING
NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN.
I'D APPRECIATE IT.
[ SHIMA ]
HEY, MR. OKUMURA,
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME RAMUNE?
YES, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
[ LINE RINGING ]
GUESS WHO.
[ AMAIMON ]
YES?
NOIHAUS FOLLOWED MY ORDERS.
HOWEVER, WHEN IT CAME
TO FINISHING THE TASK,
HE CAME UP SHORT.
COME TO TRUE CROSS ACADEMY
RIGHT AWAY.
BUT YOUR PROTECTIVE BARRIER
PREVENTS ME FROM ENTERING,
BIG BROTHER.
I'LL HAVE NOIHAUS GUIDE YOU.
WE'LL DISCUSS
THE DETAILS LATER.
UNDERSTOOD?
ROGER THAT.
[ SUGURO ]
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S DONE.
[ GASPS ]
[ RIN LAUGHS ]
I'M DIGGING IN!
HOLD IT, KIDDIES!
DON'T START WITHOUT ME!
[ BEEPING ]
[ SIGHS ]
MY FATHER AND BROTHER
ARE SO OBSESSED
WITH THIS RIN OKUMURA.
I WONDER IF HE'S
REALLY THAT SPECIAL.
I HOPE HE CAN ENTERTAIN ME
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
♪ [ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ RIN LAUGHING ]
GONNA SCOOP IT ALL UP!
NO, PLEASE!
YOU CAN'T TAKE THAT ONE!
THE CHEESE-BACON-MOCHI MONJA
IS ONE OF MY TOP THREE
MONJA MUNCHIES EVER!
I DON'T CARE IF YOU'RE
THE DIRECTOR OF THE ACADEMY.
WHEN IT COMES TO EATING,
IT'S FIRST COME, FIRST SERVED.
[ WHINING ]
YOU LITTLE DEMON!
[ RIN ]
ARE YOU GONNA KILL HIM?
[ YUKIO ]
THIS SCHOOL DOESN'T HAVE
AN EXORCIST ON THE FACULTY...
WHO CAN TAME A DEMON
OF THAT CLASS.
[ RIN ]
MY FATHER'S DEAD.
SHIRO'S DEAD.
YOU ARE ALL LIARS!