[ LAUGHING ]
IT'S TIME TO CELEBRATE
SATAN'S ASCENT
IN THE WORLD OF ASSIAH!
[ LAUGHING ]
RIN?
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ LAUGHING ]
IS THAT--
IS THAT REALLY YUKIO?
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YUKIO!
[ MEPHISTO ]
THE YOUNGER BROTHER
SACRIFICES HIMSELF...
OUT OF LOVE FOR
HIS OLDER BROTHER...
WHILE THE OLDER BROTHER
REMAINS OBLIVIOUS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THE ULTIMATE TRAGEDY...
IS ABOUT TO PLAY OUT
RIGHT BEFORE OUR EYES.
♪ [ MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
SHIT. THEY KEEP COMING.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHERE DO YOU THINK?
I'M GOING TO HELP RIN
AND THE OTHERS.
NO ONE IS ALLOWED
TO GET PAST ME.
THOSE ARE THE ORDERS
I HAVE BEEN GIVEN.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THAT CRAP!
CAN'T YOU SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[ ANGEL ]
YOUR EMINENCE, WAIT.
ARE THE RUMORS TRUE?
DO YOU INTEND
TO DESTROY GEHENNA?
THE PREPARATIONS
FOR THE MESSIAH
HAVE BEEN COMPLETED.
ALL THAT'S LEFT NOW
IS TO OPEN GEHENNA GATE.
I PROTEST.
CAUSING A MASSACRE
WITH A NUCLEAR WARHEAD?
THAT'S NOT WHAT THE ORDER
STANDS FOR.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- [ GASPS ]
YUKIO OKUMURA SHALL TAKE
THE REINS OF THIS OPERATION.
YOU MAY CONTINUE AS MY GUARD
IF YOU WISH.
YOUR EMINENCE! SIR!
PERHAPS THE VATICAN HAS MADE
A HUGE ERROR IN THE MATTER.
HOWEVER, I AM A KNIGHT
OF THE VATICAN.
EVEN IF THE WORLD IS DESTROYED,
MY SOUL REMAINS WITH
THE KNIGHTS OF THE TRUE CROSS.
COME ON!
AS LONG AS MY STRENGTH
HOLDS OUT,
I SHALL CONTINUE
TO FIGHT YOU.
OH.
YOU'RE SUCH A PAIN IN THE ASS.
WHAT NOW?
ARE YOU GIVING UP?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S GIVEN UP.
YOU WANNA KILL ME, FINE,
BUT STOP WASTING MY TIME
WITH YOUR CRAP!
COME ON, YUKIO.
WHAT THE HELL?
AND WHAT'S WITH
THOSE BLUE FLAMES?
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO INHERITED SATAN'S POWER.
- SHUT UP!
- [ GASPING ]
HOLD ON.
YOU'RE SATAN.
[ ALL ] HUH?
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
IT TOOK YOU SO DAMN LONG
TO NOTICE.
YOU WERE STARTING TO HURT
YOUR DADDY'S FEELINGS.
[ LAUGHS ]
SO THAT'S... SATAN?
WHY? WHY DID YOU TAKE OVER
YUKIO'S BODY?
SIMPLE. IT WAS READY
BEFORE YOURS WAS.
IT'S A GOOD LOOK FOR ME,
DON'T YOU THINK?
HUH?
YOU BOTH HAVE MY BLOOD
RUNNING THROUGH YOUR VEINS,
SO YOUR BODIES ARE
THE PERFECT VESSELS FOR ME.
SURE, I HAD TO WAIT A FEW YEARS
FOR YOU TO GROW UP,
BUT THE WAIT WAS WELL WORTH IT.
GET OUT OF YUKIO'S BODY,
GOD DAMN IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SHIEMI ]
RIN!
NEE!
[ COUGHS ]
RIN!
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ SATAN ]
ALWAYS INTERRUPTING.
YOU WERE RAISED BETTER
THAN THAT.
I'VE BEEN DREAMING
OF THIS MOMENT
FOR THE LAST 15 YEARS.
THE DAY I FINALLY GET TO BRING
THE WORLDS OF ASSIAH
AND GEHENNA TOGETHER...
- AND CREATE A NEW WORLD.
- A NEW WORLD?
YOU'RE CRAZY.
NOW THAT I HAVE
A DURABLE VESSEL,
I CAN MOVE FREELY AROUND ASSIAH.
AND HERE'S A HUGE GEHENNA GATE
TAILOR-MADE FOR MY NEEDS.
THIS IS A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
THE CHANCE TO MAKE
MY DREAMS COME TRUE.
SORRY, BUT I'LL BE DAMNED
IF I LET A LITTLE PIP-SQUEAK
LIKE YOU DESTROY THE GATE AGAIN.
NOW DIE.
HOLD UP!
BEFORE YOU PUNCH HIS TICKET,
HOW ABOUT YOU TAKE ME ON?
DUDE! BON!
ARE YOU CRAZY?
THAT'S SATAN.
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIM.
- SOMEONE'S GOTTA TRY.
- NOW WOULD YOU JUST SHUT UP
ALREADY?
MOVE!
[ SCREAMS ]
MR. TSUBAKI!
BRING FORTH AND PURIFY
UNHULLED RICE.
HULLED RICE.
ADD EIGHT CUPS OF DIVINE SAKE.
NOW CLAP YOUR HANDS EIGHT TIMES
AND PARTAKE IN PEACE.
THE GODS ARE LISTENING.
DIVINE SAKE OF THE HEAVENS!
[ GASPING ]
MR. TSUBAKI, YOU OKAY?
DON'T--
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU'RE NO MATCH
FOR HIS POWER.
YOU READY?
READY.
[ TOGETHER ]
GRANT US A SYMBOL
TO PROTECT US FROM HARM.
SPIRITUAL ARMOR.
GO! WE'VE GOT YOU COVERED.
HURRY UP AND GET AWAY
WHILE YOU CAN.
NAMAH, SAMANTA,
VAJRANAM, HAM MAM!
- [ BOTH ] BON!
- [ THINKING ] I SWORE I'D KILL
SATAN WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
THIS IS IT.
I CAN'T PASS IT UP.
GO, K'RIK!
- [ GASPS ]
- DON'T MESS WITH ME!
[ SCREAMING ]
- OH, NO!
- [ GROANING ]
YOU'RE ALL SO PATHETIC.
YOU'LL MAKE GOOD ASH THOUGH.
LEAVE 'EM ALONE!
[ GROANS ]
[ SHURA ]
YOU HEARD THE KID.
[ RIN ]
SHURA!
HEY, THAT'S "MS." SHURA.
- MORIYAMA.
- YES?
I CAN HANDLE THIS ON MY OWN,
BUT I NEED YOU TO GET ALL
THE WOUNDED TO SOMEPLACE SAFE.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, NEE?
NEE-EE!
NEE! NEE!
NEE! NEE! NEE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT, YOU GOING TO KILL ME
WITH YOUR TITS?
I DON'T CARE IF YOU ARE
WORKING FOR DEMONS NOW,
THAT'S WAY OUTTA LINE, CHICKEN.
THAT'S NOT YUKIO ANYMORE.
HE'S BEEN POSSESSED
BY SATAN.
FOR REAL?
YOU DARE TO CHALLENGE ME,
YOU STUPID COW?
- [ SHURA SHOUTS ]
- I'LL TURN YOU TO ASH, BITCH!
[ GASPS ]
HMM.
[ CHATTERING ]
NO WAY.
HE SAID HE WANTS TO FUSE
GEHENNA AND ASSIAH?
YEAH.
[ EXPLOSION ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
WE'RE NOT SAFE HERE.
WE SHOULD GET OUT
WHILE WE CAN.
NO. WE'RE BETTER OFF HERE.
I'M PRETTY SURE
SATAN'S GONNA STAY
CLOSE TO THAT GATE.
PRETTY SURE?
WHY WOULD HE?
BECAUSE HIS WHOLE DAMN PLAN
DEPENDS ON THAT GATE
STAYING OPEN.
HE'S GOT HIS GUARD UP
BECAUSE OF YOU.
YOU DESTROYED
THE GEHENNA GATE
ONCE BEFORE...
WHEN YOU TRIED
TO SAVE SHIRO.
HE'LL DO EVERYTHING HE CAN
TO KEEP IT OPEN NOW.
[ SHIMA CHUCKLES ]
IT'S LIKE HE'S THE "IT"
IN KICK THE CAN.
WHAT'S THAT?
HIDE AND SEEK
WITH A CAN.
THE GUY WHO'S IT
HAS TO FIND PEOPLE,
BUT HE'S ALSO GOT
TO GUARD A CAN.
IF THE CAN GETS KICKED
BY ANYONE,
THE GUY WHO'S IT LOSES.
YOU KNOW,
HE'S GOT SOMETHING THERE.
THE ODDS ARE BETTER
IF WE GO ON THE OFFENSIVE.
HE CAN'T DEFEND THE GATE
AGAINST ALL OF US, SO SOMEONE'S
BOUND TO GET THROUGH.
OKAY, BUT WHAT DO WE DO
ABOUT YUKIO?
SATAN'S WAY TOO POWERFUL.
EVEN IF WE ATTACKED HIM
ALL AT ONCE,
HE'D ANNIHILATE US.
RIGHT NOW THE BEST WE CAN DO
IS DESTROY THE GEHENNA GATE...
AND STOP ANY MORE DEMONS
FROM GETTING THROUGH.
BUT WE CAN'T JUST ABANDON YUKIO.
I WANNA SAVE HIM
AS MUCH AS YOU,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
TO SAVE SOMEONE
WHO'S BEEN POSSESSED BY SATAN,
SO YOU HAVE TO BE STRONG
AND STICK TO THE PLAN.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A WAY.
LISTEN.
WHEN MY OLD MAN WAS POSSESSED,
HE SNAPPED OUT OF IT
AT THE LAST SECOND.
I KNOW YUKIO'S SOUL
IS STILL SOMEWHERE IN THERE.
IF WE CALL OUT TO HIM,
HE'LL SNAP OUT OF IT TOO.
- RIN.
- I'M NOT GONNA GIVE UP
ON YUKIO.
HEY, HOLD UP.
WAIT. RIN!
THERE HE GOES AGAIN,
SAVING THE DAY ON HIS OWN.
[ GROANS ]
YOU SHOULDN'T
MOVE YET.
OH, THIS IS NOTHING.
I'M GOOD TO GO.
I'M NOT GONNA LET HIM
BEAT ME TO IT.
I'M GONNA KILL SATAN.
IN THE SHAPE YOU'RE IN?
WHAT GOOD ARE YOU?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHY DON'T YOU COME HERE
AND SAY THAT TO MY FACE.
CHILL OUT.
I'M NOT JUST TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
EVEN IF WE ALL WENT,
WE'D ONLY BE IN THEIR WAY,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT PAKU,
SO I'VE DECIDED
I'M NOT GONNA GO.
[ ALL GASP ]
SHE IS RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
EASY, TEACH.
THERE ARE PEOPLE HERE IN TOWN
WHO NEED YOUR TALENTS RIGHT NOW
MORE THAN EVER.
[ SHURA ]
WAIT UP.
I SAID WAIT, DAMN IT!
LET GO!
I GOTTA HELP HIM.
OKAY, CHILL OUT.
I GET IT. YOU WANNA SAVE HIM.
I'M GONNA HELP YOU.
FOR REAL?
[ SHURA ]
THE PERSON BEING THE BAIT...
IS AT THE WEST ENTRANCE
AND DISTRACTS YUKIO.
THE PERSON DOING THE AMBUSH
STANDS BY
ON TOP OF THE EAST WALL.
THE BAIT LURES YUKIO
AWAY FROM THE SQUARE;
THE AMBUSHER ATTACKS.
IF YOU GET THE CHALK,
YOU DO THE AMBUSHING.
THAT SETTLES IT.
[ GRUNTS ]
HE'S MY BROTHER.
SHOULDN'T I BE THE BAIT?
REMEMBER WHAT YUKIO
TAUGHT YOU?
HOW EXORCISTS
ARE ALL SUPPOSED
TO WORK TOGETHER?
TEAMWORK AND TRUST
ARE THE MOST IMPORTANT THINGS
IN BATTLE.
SO NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU MAKE DAMN SURE YOU SEE
YOUR END OF THE PLAN THROUGH.
- GOT THAT?
- MM-HMM.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SATAN ]
YOU SAID A NEW WORLD?
A WORLD WITH NO GEHENNA
OR ASSIAH.
WHERE HUMANS AND DEMONS
CAN LIVE TOGETHER IN PEACE.
I KNOW.
RIGHT NOW THERE'S
NO PLACE LIKE THAT,
BUT I'M SURE ONE DAY
WE CAN MAKE ONE.
IT'S NOT IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU AND I FOUND A WAY
TO UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER.
GO ON. CLOSE YOUR EYES.
TRY TO IMAGINE IT.
IT CAN'T BE THAT HARD, RIGHT?
[ SATAN, THINKING ]
WE'RE ALMOST THERE, YURI.
SOON THE WORLD WE DREAMED OF
WILL BECOME REALITY.
SO THE CHICK WITH THE CANS
IS BACK. ALONE.
SHUT UP,
YOU FOUR-EYED CHICKEN.
HUH?
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE.
YOU GONNA SIT BACK
AND LET SATAN CONTROL YOU?
COME ON, WAKE UP.
[ LAUGHS ]
CALL HIM ALL YOU WANT.
THIS VESSEL IS ALL THAT REMAINS.
WHATEVER YOU SAY, BABY.
ONE HOT WAKE-UP CALL
COMING RIGHT THE EFF UP.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ PAKU ]
DON'T CRY.
IT'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE?
WHY ARE ALL THOSE MONSTERS
POURING OUT OF THE SKY
LIKE THAT?
WE'RE ALL GONNA DIE.
THE MONSTERS ARE GONNA GET IN
HERE AND THEY'RE GONNA EAT US.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DIE.
MY FRIENDS ARE OUT THERE NOW,
AND THEY'LL PROTECT US.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SUGURO ]
NAMAH SAMANTA-BUDDHANAM BHAH!
[ KAMIKI ]
COME ON.
[ GASPS ]
HURRY UP, THIS WAY.
IZUMO!
PAKU!
I'M SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG
TO GET TO YOU.
I NEVER HAD ANY DOUBT
YOU'D BE COMING TO RESCUE US,
IZUMO.
WHERE ARE WE?
THE JAPAN BRANCH OF THE KNIGHTS
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
AFTER THE INFESTATION BEGAN,
THE VATICAN HAD US SET UP
AN EVACUATION CENTER HERE.
THESE WALLS WILL PROTECT US
FROM DEMONIC ATTACKS.
HEY, BON,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HAVE EITHER OF YOU GUYS
SEEN MORIYAMA?
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER IN A WHILE.
MAYBE SHE GOT LOST
IN THE EVACUATION.
DID YOU TRY CALLING HER?
NO. SHE DOESN'T HAVE
A CELL PHONE.
OKAY, NOW I'M WORRIED.
[ GRUNTING ]
- [ GROWLS ]
- [ GASPS ]
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
MS. SHURA.
[ AMAIMON ]
THAT WOMAN IS HOLDING UP
QUITE NICELY AGAINST FATHER.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
SHE'S STILL MORTAL.
SHE CAN ONLY TAKE
SO MUCH PUNISHMENT.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
OKAY, IS THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
NO, I GOT THIS
FOR YOU TOO.
WHAT A PAIN IN THE ASS.
TRYING TO GET THE DROP ON ME?
[ SHURA, THINKING ]
DAMN IT. HE'S NOT AS DUMB
AS I THOUGHT. WHATEVER.
I STILL NEED HIM
TO FOLLOW ME...
OR I'M TOTALLY SCREWED!
KIRIGAKURE ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE.
SNAKE FORM,
WHITE SERPENT ATTACK!
[ SNARLING ]
[ PANTING ]
[ SCREAMS, GRUNTS ]
SHURA!
[ SHIEMI ]
STOP IT!
WELL, WELL, LOOKS LIKE
WE HAVE A VISITOR.
- SHIEMI.
- PLEASE STOP, I BEG YOU.
YUKI WOULD NEVER DO
SOMETHING THIS CRUEL.
AND WHO ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE?
ONE OF HIS LITTLE FRIENDS?
YES. HE'S REALLY PRECIOUS TO ME.
SO PLEASE GIVE HIM BACK!
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH!
NEE!
[ AMAIMON ]
SHE JUST BLOCKED
FATHER'S FLAMES.
THAT'S JAPANESE ROWAN.
IT WON'T CATCH FIRE...
EVEN IF YOU THROW IT
IN A WHITE-HOT OVEN
AND TURN THE HEAT UP TO 11.
GOOD CALL ON HER PART,
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- [ CRACKING ]
- [ GASPS ]
[ GROANING ]
NEE!
YOU'RE LITTLE PET
CAN BLOCK MY FLAMES,
BUT WITHOUT IT
YOU DON'T STAND
MUCH OF A CHANCE, DO YOU?
YU... KI, STOP.
- SHIEMI!
- [ GROWLING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
GOD DAMN IT, LET HER GO!
IDIOT. YOU'RE EARLY.
AHA, SO THERE YOU ARE.
AND WITH EVERYONE ELSE
OUT OF THE WAY,
WHY DON'T WE SETTLE THIS
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT
MY LITTLE BROTHER.
WHAT?
YUKIO, I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE.
COME ON, WAKE UP.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU REALLY THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO SAVE YOUR BROTHER?
- HOW TOUCHING.
- [ GRUNTS ]
WAKE UP, YUKIO.
IT'S ME--
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
YOUR BROTHER BELONGS TO ME NOW.
STOP CALLING HIM.
HE CAN'T HEAR YOU ANYMORE.
[ GURGLES ]
I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME, YUKIO.
YUKIO!
[ ECHOING ]
YUKIO.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO GIVE UP.
[ THINKING ]
YUKIO.
COME ON, OPEN YOUR EYES!
YUKIO!
[ METALLIC CLINKING ]
[ GASPS ]
RIN.
RIN!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ YOUNG YUKIO ]
I WON'T LET YOU GO.
YOU DON'T REALLY THINK
YOU CAN ESCAPE, DO YOU?
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU REALLY HATE RIN.
RIN NEVER KNEW
WHAT WAS GOING ON AROUND US,
BUT EVER SINCE I CAN REMEMBER,
I'VE ALWAYS SEEN
THE DEMONS IN THE DARK.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'RE LYING.
AS LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER,
RIN ALWAYS DID
THE THINGS I NEVER COULD.
- [ GASPS ]
- EVEN WITHOUT TRYING,
RIN ALWAYS GETS THE THINGS
I CAN NEVER HAVE.
IT'S SO UNFAIR!
I HATE RIN.
IF ONLY HE WERE DEAD.
- IF ONLY HE WAS NEVER BORN!
- NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
I-- I--
RIN.
[ GASPS ]
HELP ME, RIN.
[ GROANING ]
YUKIO!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
RIN! RIN!
[ GASPING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SHOUTS ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
- [ SHURA ]
RIN!
- [ GASPING ]
[ YUKIO WEEPING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SATAN ]
I NEVER THOUGHT
YOU'D REGAIN YOUR SENSES.
BUT I'M NOT LETTING YOU
GET AWAY.
YOU BELONG TO ME.
GO AHEAD, FINISH HIM OFF.
KILL HIM.
WITHOUT HIM AROUND,
WE CAN FINALLY CREATE
THE WORLD WE'VE DREAMED OF.
[ CRYING ]
DO IT!
- DO IT!
- [ CRYING CONTINUES ]
NOW!
I WON'T!
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
I'M GOING TO KILL US BOTH!
YOU BASTARD!
YUKI... O.
GODDAMN RETCHED PRIEST!
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN KILL ME
BY COMMITTING SUICIDE?
RIDICULOUS!
I PROMISED MY FATHER
I'D PROTECT MY BROTHER!
IF SUICIDE'S THE ONLY WAY
TO SAVE HIM AND EVERYONE ELSE,
THEN I WILL KILL MYSELF!
[ SATAN ]
STOP! DON'T DO IT!
IF YOU DIE, THE WORLD
YURI AND I DREAMED OF
WILL DIE WITH YOU!
[ SHOUTING ]
SHUT UP.
LET SOMEONE ELSE
BE THE HERO FOR ONCE.
YOU THINK KILLING SATAN
BY OFFING YOURSELF'S
THE BEST YOU CAN COME UP WITH?
- BULLSHIT!
- [ GASPS ]
YOU KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
WHEN DAD DIED,
BOTH OF US WERE LEFT BEHIND.
AND I JUST--
I NEVER EVER WANNA FEEL
THAT WAY AGAIN.
[ SOBS ]
I KNOW, RIN.
[ HISSING ]
[ SOBBING ]
I'M SORRY, RIN.
I'M SORRY.
[ RUMBLING ]
CRAP. NOW WHAT?
[ SATAN LAUGHING ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THAT'S SATAN.
WHAT A SURPRISE.
I NEVER DREAMED
I COULD BE KNOCKED OFF
MY FEET LIKE THAT.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
MY DREAM IS NOT QUITE OVER!
[ SHRIEKING ]
- WHAT THE HELL?
- IT'S THE GEHENNA GATE.
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ MEPHISTO ]
THE WAR BETWEEN THE DEMONS
AND HUMANKIND...
IS APPROACHING ITS CLIMAX!
PREPARE YOURSELVES,
MY YOUNG BROTHERS.
LET'S SEE HOW YOU FARE IN BATTLE
AGAINST OUR RAMPAGING FATHER.
♪ [ WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
[ YUKIO ]
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT...
MAYBE IT WASN'T RIGHT
THAT YOU AND I WERE BORN?
[ RIN GRUNTS ]
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT LIGHT?
[ MEPHISTO ]
THE CONTRACT IS SEALED.
NOW THEN,
I BID YOU ADIEU.