[ BIRDS TWITTERING ]
THEY'RE ANNOUNCING
OUR TEST SCORES TODAY.
OH, BY THE WAY,
HAVE YOU MADE
ANY NEW FRIENDS YET?
MM-HMM.
I'D BETTER GET GOING.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
[ SIGHS ]
HAVE I MADE FRIENDS?
[ SUGURO ]
SHE'S YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
ISN'T SHE?
YOU GOT THE WRONG IDEA
ABOUT US, MAN.
SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU GUYS JUST FRIENDS, HUH?
WHAT? ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NO.
[ WHIMPERS ]
DON'T CRY, SHIEMI.
THERE'S NO TIME...
'CAUSE TODAY'S THE DAY.
I'M GONNA GO OUT
AND MAKE SOME NEW FRIENDS.
MISS KAMIKI, MISS PAKU.
HELLO. I WAS WONDERING--
[ SHRIEKS ]
OW. THAT HURT.
MISS MORIYAMA?
YOU KLUTZ.
[ WHIMPERS ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
MM-HMM.
TRY TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
WAIT UP, IZUMO.
[ RIN ]
SHIEMI?
EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT YOU DOING DOWN THERE?
UM, NOTHING.
I'M FINE.
I CAN'T DEPEND ON RIN.
I'VE GOT TO DO THIS ON MY OWN.
♪ [ MAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE ]
LISTEN UP.
SUMMER VACATION
IS LESS THAN A MONTH
AND A HALF AWAY,
BUT BEFORE THE BREAK,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE TAKING...
THIS YEAR'S
EXWIRE AUTHORIZATION EXAM.
ESQUIRE EXAM?
WHAT THE HECK'S THAT?
NO, EXWIRE.
HUH?
A CANDIDATE FOR BECOMING
AN EXORCIST.
HUH.
I WANT EVERYONE
TO KEEP IN MIND...
THAT ONCE YOU'RE PROMOTED
TO EXWIRE...
YOU'LL BE SUBJECTED
TO MORE SPECIALIZED
COMBAT TRAINING.
THE EXAM WON'T BE EASY TO PASS,
THEREFORE, STARTING MONDAY,
WE'RE OFFERING
A WEEKLONG BOOT CAMP
TO PREPARE YOU FOR THE EXAM.
A BOOT CAMP?
SINCE ATTENDING THE CAMP
ISN'T MANDATORY,
INDICATE WHETHER OR NOT
YOU'LL BE PARTICIPATING
ON THE FORM.
IF YOU ARE, PLEASE INDICATE
THE MEISTER, OR TITLE,
THAT YOU'D LIKE TO ACQUIRE,
AND TURN THE FORM IN BY MONDAY.
A MEISTER OR A TITLE?
HEY, COULD YOU TELL ME
WHAT A MEISTER IS?
HUH?
UH, COME ON.
HELP ME OUT HERE.
PLEASE.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
YOU WANT TO BE AN EXORCIST,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS?
SERIOUSLY,
WHAT'S WITH YOU?
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU REALLY ARE
TOTALLY CLUELESS,
- AREN'T YOU, OKUMURA?
- FINE. I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
SO ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME
OR WHAT?
I'LL TELL YOU.
IT'S A TECHNICAL
QUALIFICATION...
THAT'S REQUIRED
TO BECOME AN EXORCIST.
IT'S A TITLE GIVEN TO THOSE
WHO'VE PROVED THEY'VE GOT
GREAT SKILLS.
THERE ARE FIVE MEISTERS IN ALL.
KNIGHT, DRAGOON, TAMER,
ARIA AND DOCTOR.
AS LONG AS YOU'VE ACQUIRED
AT LEAST ONE OF THOSE,
YOU CAN BECOME AN EXORCIST.
OH, OKAY.
I THINK I GET IT NOW.
NO ONE SAID
YOU COULD SIT WITH US.
THE OTHER THING IS,
YOUR STYLE OF COMBAT
WILL DIFFER...
DEPENDING ON WHICH MEISTER
YOU ARE.
SWEET. THANKS FOR EXPLAINING,
KONEKOMARU.
WHICH ONE ARE YOU GOING FOR?
WELL, SHIMA AND I
ARE GOING TO TRY
FOR ARIA.
HMM? ARIA?
ARIA'S A MEISTER
THAT BATTLES DEMONS...
BY RECITING PASSAGES
FROM THE BIBLE
AND OTHER SACRED SCRIPTURES.
BON HERE'S GONNA GO
FOR BOTH ARIA AND DRAGOON...
'CAUSE HE'S ALL HARD CORE
AND EVERYTHING.
WOW. THAT'S OUR BON.
DO NOT CALL ME BON!
ACTUALLY, OUR INSTRUCTOR,
MR. OKUMURA, HAS TWO MEISTERS--
DOCTOR AND DRAGOON.
HUH. YUKIO KICKS BUTT.
HMM. I WONDER WHICH OF THOSE
I SHOULD GO FOR.
THIS DRAGOON-- WHAT IS IT?
[ LOUD THUMP ]
HUH?
MY GOD!
YOU ARE SUCH A PAIN.
A DRAGOON'S A MEISTER
WHO FIGHTS WITH FIREARMS.
AND A KNIGHT'S
A MEISTER WHO FIGHTS
WITH A FRIGGIN' SWORD.
[ SHIMA CHUCKLES ]
SEE? EVEN WITH
ALL THE GRUMBLING,
BON CAN STILL BE HELPFUL.
[ SUGURO ]
SHUT UP!
- BACK UP.
YOU SAY SWORD?
- MM-HMM.
THE MEISTERS WHO SPECIALIZE
IN SWORD FIGHTING
ARE CALLED KNIGHTS.
OKAY. THEN I'M GONNA BE
A KNIGHT.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS SEE YOU
CARRYING THAT SWORD AROUND.
YEP. IT'S SORT OF LIKE
A KEEPSAKE FROM MY DAD.
RIN SEEMS LIKE HE'S HAPPIER
WHEN HE'S HANGING OUT
WITH THE OTHER BOYS.
I'VE GOT TO BE STRONG THOUGH.
BUT WHAT SHOULD I DO?
RIN AND YUKI
HELPED ME GET IN HERE.
NO. IT'S NOT THEIR JOB
TO TAKE CARE OF ME.
IT'S MINE.
ALL RIGHT.
I WILL NOW SUMMON A DEMON.
- WHOA.
- WATCH YOUR STEP.
IF THE MAGIC CIRCLE IS BROKEN,
IT WILL LOSE ITS EFFECT.
NOW, TO SUMMON A DEMON,
YOU'LL NEED
A DROP OF YOUR BLOOD...
AND A SUITABLE INVOCATION.
SON OF TYPHOEUS AND ECHIDNA,
HEAR MY CALL AND SHOW YOURSELF.
[ GASPING ]
[ LOW GROANING ]
IS THAT A NABERIUS?
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE.
EW, SULFUR.
SUMMONING A DEMON
TO USE AS A FAMILIAR
IS A RARE TRAIT.
NOT EVERYONE IS CAPABLE.
NOW, TO TAME A DEMON,
YOU MUST HAVE A STRONG WILL
AND UNSHAKABLE NERVE.
HAVING A NATURAL TALENT FOR IT
IS ALSO VALUABLE.
HUH?
TODAY I'M GOING TO TEST YOU...
TO SEE IF ANYONE HERE
HAS THIS TALENT.
- A TEST?
- AT THE BEGINNING OF CLASS,
I HANDED OUT PIECES OF PAPER
WITH A COPY OF THE MAGIC CIRCLE.
PLACE A DROP OF BLOOD ON IT
AND CHANT WHATEVER WORDS
MAY COME TO MIND.
I HUMBLY APPEAL TO THEE,
OH GODDESS INARI.
GRANT MY REQUEST.
LEAVE NOT MY PRAYERS TO THEE
UNFULFILLED.
WHOA! THAT'S SO
UNBELIEVABLY COOL.
A PAIR OF WHITE FOXES.
NICELY DONE, MISS KAMIKI.
IZUMO, THAT'S AMAZING.
I TRIED,
BUT I DIDN'T GET ANYTHING.
THAT FIGURES.
I COME FROM A LONG LINE
OF SHRINE MAIDENS.
THIS ISN'T WORKING.
I CAN'T DO IT.
ME NEITHER.
HMM.
MISS KAMIKI'S AMAZING.
HERE GOES.
UM, I'D LIKE TO TRY IT NEXT.
COME ON, BOY.
OR SOMETHING.
HMM.
NEE!
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
THAT LOOKS LIKE A BABY GREENMAN.
EXCELLENT, MISS MORIYAMA.
EXCELLENT.
[ HUFFS ]
N-NICE TO MEET YOU.
NEE! NEE.
[ GIGGLES ]
THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO TALK TO HER.
UM, HEY, MISS KAMIKI?
I-I SUMMONED
MY FAMILIAR TOO.
ADORABLE. IT'S LIKE
SO UNBELIEVABLY TINY...
AND RIDICULOUSLY CUTE,
LIKE A PEANUT.
HUH? REALLY?
YOU THINK HE'S CUTE?
OH, THANK YOU.
LOOKS AS THOUGH WE HAVE
OUR TAMER CANDIDATES
FOR THIS CLASS.
NOW THEN, TAMERS
ARE VALUABLE IN COMBAT.
THE ABILITY TO CONTROL DEMONS
IS EXTREMELY RARE
AMONG EXORCISTS.
A DEMON WILL NOT OBEY
IF IT PERCEIVES ITS MASTER
TO BE WEAK.
IF ITS MASTER LACKS WILLPOWER,
THE DEMON WILL ATTACK THEM.
OH.
NEE!
WE'RE OKAY, RIGHT?
AS I MENTIONED EARLIER,
ONCE YOU BREAK THE CIRCLE,
YOU RELEASE THE FAMILIAR
FROM YOUR CONTROL
AND IT VANISHES.
SO IF YOU EVER FEEL
LIKE YOU'RE IN DANGER,
SIMPLY TEAR UP THE PAPER.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
THAT'S ALL FOR TODAY.
CLASS DISMISSED.
NEE?
I WON'T MAKE YOU DISAPPEAR,
I PROMISE.
IS IT OKAY
IF I CALL YOU NEE?
NEE.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
UH, S-SURE.
HEY, MISS KAMIKI?
UM--
IZUMO, SHE'S CALLING YOU.
IGNORE HER, PAKU.
KEEP WALKING.
THAT GIRL'S SO ANNOYING.
[ SHIEMI ]
WAIT UP!
WAIT!
WAIT! WAIT!
[ GROWLS ]
WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME AROUND?
OKAY, YOU SUMMONED A FAMILIAR.
BIG DEAL.
DO YOU THINK
THAT MAKES YOU SPECIAL NOW?
HUH?
UM, I JUST--
UM, I, UH--
I'D LIKE...
TO-- TO--
WOULD YOU PLEASE
BE MY FRIEND?
OH.
HUH?
YOU SEE, I, UH,
I'VE NEVER HAD
ANY FRIENDS BEFORE.
SO, UM--
HMM.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
- HUH?
I SAID ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL BE FRIENDS FROM NOW ON.
REALLY?
[ CHUCKLES ]
- I'M SO HAPPY.
- GOOD. HANG ON TO THIS
FOR ME, OKAY?
I GET TIRED EASY
'CAUSE I'M NOT THAT STRONG.
AFTER ALL, FRIENDS ARE SUPPOSED
TO HELP EACH OTHER OUT.
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR,
RIGHT?
FRIENDS HELP EACH OTHER.
[ GIGGLES ]
IZUMO, ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
SHE SEEMS HAPPY ENOUGH,
SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
HUH?
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
SHIEMI'S CARRYING
POLKA BROW'S STUFF LIKE
SHE'S HER MAID OR SOMETHING.
POLKA BROW?
[ LAUGHS ]
HE MEANS MISS KAMIKI.
[ SUGURO ]
THEY'RE JUST MESSING AROUND.
HERE. PASS THESE OUT
FOR ME, WILL YOU?
UH-HUH.
WE'RE USING VALERIANA
IN OUR NEXT PHARMACEUTICS CLASS.
MAKE SURE AND GET ME SOME, OKAY?
UH-HUH.
MELON BREAD AND FRUIT MILK.
GOT IT?
UH-HUH.
UNBELIEVABLE.
POOR SHIEMI.
SHE'S RUNNING AROUND
LIKE AN ERRAND GIRL.
WHAT?
YEAH.
NOTHING. SO WHY ARE WE HAVING
BOOT CAMP IN OUR DORM ANYWAY?
IT'S CONVENIENT,
AND BESIDES, WE'RE
THE ONLY ONES LIVING HERE...
SO WE WON'T
BE DISTURBING ANYONE.
IT'S GOING TO BE FINE.
HUH?
GOOD MORNING.
YOUR CLASS HAS ARRIVED.
[ YUKIO ]
GOOD MORNING, EVERYONE.
SERIOUSLY? THIS THING
LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
OUT OF A HORROR MOVIE.
WOW, IT'S SO CREEPY.
AND UGLY.
WAS THIS THE BEST PLACE
WE COULD FIND TO DO THIS?
OH. TAKE IT.
UH-HUH.
[ GROWLS ]
MISS MORIYAMA,
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO,
JUST SAY SO.
HUH? OH, NO,
I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
I'M JUST HELPING OUT A FRIEND
BECAUSE THAT'S
WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR.
UH, OKAY.
TIME'S UP.
TURN YOUR PAPERS OVER
AND HAND THEM IN, PLEASE.
[ ALL GRUMBLING ]
WHEW. THANK GOD
IT'S OVER.
THAT TOOK
FOREVER.
I'M GONNA GO GET
SOME AIR. LATER.
YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
I WANT EVERYONE UP
BY 6:00 A.M. TOMORROW.
THAT'LL GIVE US AN HOUR
BEFORE WE START CLASS...
TO GO OVER THE ANSWERS
TO THE TEST.
[ GROANS ]
DEMON. SADIST.
PAKU, LET'S GO TAKE A BATH.
MM-HMM.
OH, I WANNA GO.
[ PAKU ]
I HOPE THE BATHTUB'S BIG.
[ KAMIKI ]
I DON'T CARE.
I JUST WANNA SOAK.
[ PAKU ]
YOU'VE ALWAYS LOVED
TAKING A BATH.
[ KAMIKI ]
WELL, OF COURSE.
I AM A GIRL.
[ LAUGHS ]
THREE GIRLS TAKING A BATH.
TOGETHER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, GUYS,
WE BUST ASS OVER THERE
AND HAVE OURSELVES A PEEK?
HELLO? YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE A MONK, SHIMA.
YOU'RE GETTING BACK
INTO YOUR BAD HABITS AGAIN.
AW, SHUT IT.
YOU GUYS ARE BOTH JUST
AS INTERESTED AS I AM.
[ YUKIO ] EXCUSE ME.
YOUR TEACHER'S
SITTING RIGHT HERE.
COME ON, LOOSEN UP
A LITTLE.
YOU MIGHT BE OUR TEACHER,
BUT YOU'RE ALSO A FRESHMAN,
JUST LIKE US.
IT'S MY POLICY NOT TO ENGAGE
IN FRIVOLOUS PURSUITS.
UH.
[ PAKU ]
THIS IS IT.
WOW. THIS IS GREAT!
I'VE NEVER TAKEN A BATH
WITH FRIENDS BEFORE.
- OH, SORRY.
- HMM?
COULD YOU WAIT OUT HERE?
- WELL, CAN'T I COME IN?
- NO, YOU CAN'T.
I'M SHY, AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO SEE ME NAKED.
HUH?
IF YOU WERE MY FRIEND,
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
OH, I KNOW.
INSTEAD OF WAITING OUT HERE,
GO TO THE STORE
AND BUY ME SOME FRUIT MILK.
I WANT TO DRINK IT
AFTER MY BATH.
[ FOOTSTEPS RECEDING ]
MM-HMM.
'KAY. THANKS.
HEY, WHAT YOU DOING?
OH, NOTHING.
JUST GOING TO GO GET
SOME FRUIT MILK.
HEY!
[ GASPS ]
LISTEN, STOP DOING THAT.
DOING WHAT?
THAT! ACTING LIKE
HER ERRAND GIRL.
STOP IT.
I'M NOT HER ERRAND GIRL.
I'M JUST HELPING OUT
MY FRIEND.
YOU BELIEVE THAT?
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU KNOW YOU DON'T.
I-- I'M TIRED
OF BEING THE ONE
WHO ALWAYS NEEDS HELP.
ALWAYS HIDING BEHIND OTHERS.
I JUST WANT TO--
TO BE LIKE YOU AND YUKI.
TO BE STRONG ENOUGH TO HELP
SOMEONE OUT FOR A CHANGE.
SHE IS THE FIRST FRIEND
I'VE EVER HAD IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
YOU DON'T GET IT
'CAUSE YOU'VE ALWAYS
BEEN STRONG.
YOU'VE ALWAYS HAD FRIENDS.
UH, HEY, HOLD UP.
UH.
[ SHOUTS ]
THANK GOODNESS.
AT LEAST THE BATHTUB'S CLEAN.
IT'S LIKE THE HAUNTED
MANSION IN HERE.
AM I RIGHT?
HEY, IZUMO?
HMM?
WHY ARE YOU BEING MEAN
TO HER?
HUH?
WELL, WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES IT MAKE?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S
REALLY MY FRIEND OR ANYTHING.
IF SHE WANTS TO DO
WHATEVER I TELL HER TO,
HEY, THAT'S HER DEAL.
OH, BUT YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
WHEN YOU DECIDED
TO COME TO THE CRAM SCHOOL,
I WAS SO HAPPY.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
SO MUCH FUN.
BUT I'M BARELY KEEPING UP
ON ALL THE CLASSES AS IT IS.
DON'T WORRY.
I PROMISE
I'LL LOOK AFTER YOU.
DID YOU HEAR?
KAMIKI FREAKED OUT AGAIN.
SHE SAYS SHE SAW A GHOST.
SHE'S CREEPY.
I BET
SHE'S LYING.
SHE'S GOT NO FRIENDS
AND JUST WANTS ATTENTION.
YEAH, SHE'S A LONER.
[ ALL GIGGLING ]
WAIT UP, MISS KAMIKI.
I'M ON THE COMMITTEE TOO.
LET ME HELP YOU.
IF YOU HANG AROUND ME,
MISS PAKU, THEY'RE JUST GONNA
MAKE FUN OF YOU TOO.
HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
LIKE ANYONE CARES WHAT THEY SAY.
I'M NOT VERY NICE.
JUST SAYIN'.
[ GIGGLES ]
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO, PAKU,
IS STICK WITH ME,
AND YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN, IZUMO?
HMM?
I THINK I SHOULD QUIT GOING
TO CRAM SCHOOL.
WHAT?
I CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH THE CLASSES, AND--
AND I CAN'T SEE MYSELF
RISKING MY LIFE IN BATTLE.
BUT-- BUT I SAID I'D--
HMM-MM. THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
BESIDES, I DON'T LIKE HOW YOU
MAKE FUN OF THE PEOPLE IN CLASS
WHO TRY TO DO THEIR BEST.
I'M SORRY.
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO TELL YOU,
BUT I COULDN'T.
THAT'S THE THING.
A REAL FRIEND WOULD'VE
TOLD YOU EARLIER.
SORRY.
HUH?
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE MISS KAMIKI
AND MISS PAKU.
I GOT THIS.
GO TELL YUKIO.
RIN'S SO AMAZING.
HE DIDN'T HESITATE.
HE JUST TOOK OFF.
HOW CAN HE BE SO BRAVE?
[ SCREAMING ]
DON'T GO. DON'T LEAVE!
I WANNA GO TOO!
- [ GRUNTS ]
- PAKU!
A GHOUL'S TEMPTAINT
HAS TO BE TREATED RIGHT AWAY...
OR ELSE--
I HUMBLY APPEAL TO THEE,
OH, GODDESS INARI.
GRANT MY REQUEST.
LEAVE NOT MY PRAYERS
TO THEE UNFULFILLED.
[ SNARLS ]
WHAT DO I DO?
I HAVE TO SAVE HER.
PAKU'S THE ONLY FRIEND
I'VE GOT, AND I'M NOT GONNA
LET HER GET HURT.
[ PAKU ]
HMM-MM. THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
- [ GASPS ]
- I DON'T LIKE IT--
HUH? HOW DARE YOU.
YOUR HEART IS WEAK.
WHAT?
YOU ARE NOT WORTHY
OF OUR HELP.
- [ GASPS ]
- [ GRUNTING ]
TEAR UP THE PAPER.
DO IT!
GOOD.
[ ROARS ]
STAY BACK.
I GOT IT.
DAMN IT.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I CAN'T DRAW MY SWORD
IN FRONT OF HER.
HURRY THE HELL UP, YUKIO.
- [ SHIEMI ]
RIN!
- HEY!
[ SHIEMI ]
PAKU!
YOU KEEP THE GHOUL BUSY, RIN.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF MISS PAKU.
- COME ON,
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
- HUH?
THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
[ SNARLING ]
IT LOOKS A LOT
LIKE A BURN.
[ KAMIKI ]
IT'S A GHOUL'S TEMPTAINT.
IT'LL GO NECROTIC SOON.
THEN THERE'S NO TIME
TO MOVE HER.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING NOW.
MY YOUNG PRINCE.
[ GASPS, YELLS ]
[ SHOUTING ]
RIN!
I'M OKAY.
WHAT DO I DO?
TO TREAT A BURN
I'M GONNA NEED--
MR. SANCHO!
HUH?
WHERE AM I GONNA FIND SOME?
NEE!
- YEAH, NEE?
- [ GRUNTING ]
OH! NICE JOB, NEE.
YOU BROUGHT ME SOME
MR. SANCHO.
NO, THAT'S AN ALOE VERA PLANT.
WAIT. WHY IS ALOE VERA
SPROUTING FROM YOUR FAMILIAR?
[ ROARS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
FORGIVE ME.
I ONLY DO...
AS MY MASTER
COMMANDS ME TO.
HE MEAN SATAN?
NO USE.
I DON'T HAVE A CHANCE
AGAINST HIM LIKE THIS.
CAN'T HOLD ON.
- [ YUKIO ]
RIN!
- [ GUNFIRE ]
- GET BACK HERE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
ARE YOU HURT?
YOU'RE LATE!
BUT I STILL MADE IT,
DIDN'T I?
SHIEMI, HOW'S MISS PAKU?
OKAY, I THINK.
NEE.
YOU DID GOOD.
WHO KNOWS
WHAT MIGHT HAVE HAPPENED
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN HERE.
[ BOTH GASP ]
MISS PAKU!
[ GROANS ]
MISS MORIYAMA?
THANKS A LOT...
FOR SAVING ME.
UH-HUH.
[ CRYING ]
HMM?
HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
DON'T LOOK AT ME!
I'M SO ASHAMED.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE
SEEING ME LIKE THIS.
I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING.
I COULDN'T EVEN HELP
THE ONLY FRIEND I EVER HAD.
AND NOW SHE HATES ME.
JUST PUT IT ON
AND GET GOING.
[ FOOTSTEPS RECEDING ]
[ GROWLING ]
SO YOU FAILED.
[ GROWLS ]
WAS THAT A HOWL?
OR PERHAPS YOU'RE AMUSED
AT HOW FAR I'VE FALLEN
TO BECOME A DEMON'S LAPDOG.
♪ [ MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
WOULD YOU MIND EXPLAINING
WHY YOU'RE NAKED?
IT JUST HAPPENED?
NEVER MIND.
JUST GET EVERYONE
OUT OF HERE.
[ KAMIKI ]
I'D RATHER DIE THAN BE FRIENDS
WITH THESE LOSERS.
[ SUGURO ]
WITH A PERSONALITY LIKE THAT,
NO WONDER YOU'RE ALL ALONE.
[ YUKIO ]
YOU NEED TO LEARN TO GET ALONG.
EXORCISTS DO NOT GO
INTO BATTLE ALONE.