[YUKIO]
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE YOU
SPREAD OUT...
TO FIND AND LIGHT SOME LANTERNS
THAT ARE HIDDEN
SOMEWHERE IN THE FOREST.
WHOEVER CAN KEEP THEIR LANTERN
LIT AND RETURN IT TO BASE CAMP
IN THE NEXT THREE DAYS...
WILL BE ELIGIBLE TO GO
ON ACTUAL COMBAT MISSIONS.
[ALL GASP]
HOWEVER, THERE ARE ONLY
THREE LANTERNS OUT THERE.
THEREFORE, THERE ARE ONLY THREE
SLOTS OPEN TO GO ON MISSIONS.
YOU'LL BLOW YOUR COVER
IN THAT BIG, DARK FOREST,
SO YOU'D BETTER NOT
BE FLAMING UP OUT THERE, KID.
[GASPS]
I WAS THINKING THIS DRILL
IS ACTUALLY DESIGNED...
TO MAKE US COMPETE,
BUT THEN IF WE START
DOING THAT--
WE ARE GONNA BE
AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
READY.
[GUNSHOT]
[PANTING]
[FLUTTERING]
HUH?
WHOA! WHERE'D ALL THE MOTHS
COME FROM?
[THINKING]
BLOOD-SUCKING MOTHS.
THEY MUST BE
SOME KIND OF CHUCHI.
I HUMBLY APPEAL TO THEE,
OH, GODDESS INARI.
GRANT MY REQUEST.
LEAVE NOT MY PRAYERS TO THEE
UNFULFILLED.
- [GROWLING]
- HEY, NEE, I NEED
SOME BUG-REPELLENT ROUX.
- NEE!
- [GASPS]
NEE? NEE, NEE, NEE, NEE!
[GASPS]
NEE?
- [GASPS]
- [SHIEMI SCREAMING]
THAT'S SHIEMI.
SHIEMI, WHERE ARE YOU?
SHIEMI! SHIEMI!
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[RIN]
GET LOST!
[CELL PHONES RINGING]
MINE'S RINGING TOO.
HMM.
IT'S KONEKOMARU.
HE SAYS HE FOUND
A LANTERN.
[BOTH GASP]
"I CAN'T DO THIS ALONE."
HE'S ASKING FOR HELP.
[SHIMA]
WHOA.
UH, YEAH.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD
LUG THIS BACK ALL BY YOURSELF.
ONCE I SAW IT, I REALIZED
WE MUST HAVE MISUNDERSTOOD
THE REAL PURPOSE OF THIS DRILL.
YEAH. FOR THIS DRILL,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO HELP
EACH OTHER AFTER ALL.
[CHANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[SHIEMI]
WOW, RIN, YOU'RE STRONG.
[SHIMA]
OKUMURA, WHAT PLANET
DO YOU COME FROM?
UH, HANG ON,
'CAUSE WE'RE DOING THIS.
UH, OKAY.
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH SHOUTING]
IT'S SO HIGH!
ALL RIGHT, GIDDYAP!
[ROARING]
[GROWLING]
HERE IT COMES!
OVER HERE!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TEASE IT!
[SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS]
KAHN!
[CHANTING]
WE DID IT!
WELL, NOW THAT
THAT'S OVER WITH.
[CREAKING]
UH--
OH.
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING]
[SUGURO]
OKUMURA!
[THINKING]
OH, CRAP.
I CAN'T MOVE.
- RIN!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU
AFTER I KICK ITS ASS.
EVERYTHING'S COOL.
JUST GO.
THAT SON OF A--
YOU'RE ALWAYS DOING THAT.
[CHUCKLES]
MY BAD.
YOU DUMBASS!
I'M GONNA HELP YOU,
LIKE IT OR NOT.
HUH?
SHIMA, GIVE ME
YOUR K'RIK.
HERE YOU GO.
JUST BE CAREFUL WITH IT, 'KAY?
EVERYONE ELSE, GET READY TO RUN.
[GROWLS]
NAMAH, SAMANTA, VAJRANAM.
HAM MAM!
[CHITTERING]
[GROANING]
COME, K'RIK!
WHOA, DUDE, AWESOME.
COME ON, HURRY UP.
OKAY.
[GRUNTING]
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO,
SO GET MOVING.
HUH?
[SUGURO]
RUN!
[ROARING]
[RIN]
WHAT HAPPENED?
I THOUGHT YOU KILLED IT!
♪ [MEN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[ALL PANTING]
[MIWA]
I THINK IT STOPPED CHASING US.
[PANTING CONTINUES]
[SHIMA]
THANK GOD.
HEY, SUGURO,
THANKS A LOT, MAN.
I WAS JUST PAYING
YOU BACK, IS ALL.
FOR WHAT?
I DID IT BECAUSE YOU SAVED
MY LIFE ONCE BEFORE.
I DID IT 'CAUSE YOU WANT
THE SAME THING I DO--
TO DEFEAT SATAN.
AND BECAUSE YOU HAD THE GUTS
TO ADMIT IT
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE.
YEAH, WELL, A MORON LIKE ME
DOESN'T REALLY THINK TOO HARD
BEFORE SAYING STUFF LIKE THAT.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE A MORON.
HUH?
BUT STILL, YOU'RE BEING STUPID
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE
EVERYTHING ON BY YOURSELF.
YOU'VE GOT FRIENDS.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
[SHIMA] YOU GO, BON.
COULDN'T HAVE SAID IT
BETTER MYSELF.
IF YOU'RE GONNA TAKE SATAN ON,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY GOING
TO NEED SOME HELP.
I'M A WIMP,
BUT I GOT YOUR BACK.
COURSE, IF THERE'S
GONNA BE BUGS INVOLVED,
I WON'T DO YOU MUCH GOOD.
- YOU GUYS ARE--
- RIN, WE'RE HERE FOR YOU.
[SIGHS]
RIGHT.
I HATE TO SAY IT, SHIMA,
BUT THIS TIME
YOU WERE TOTALLY USELESS.
HEY! COME ON,
EASY, BON.
I'M DOING THE BEST I CAN,
CONSIDERING.
[LAUGHING]
[THINKING]
WHAT IF EVERYONE FOUND OUT
I WAS THE SON OF SATAN?
BUGS AREN'T THAT BAD.
WHAT WOULD THEY THINK
OF ME THEN?
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN?
OH, THANK GOD!
WE FINALLY MADE IT BACK ALIVE.
CONGRATS, GUYS.
YOU ALL MADE IT BACK
IN ONE PIECE.
WHAT THE HELL?
HOW'D YOU GUYS FINISH
THE MISSION ON YOUR OWN?
I JUST MADE MY FAMILIARS
DRAG THE LANTERN BACK.
TAKARA GOT HERE FIRST THOUGH.
IT TOOK THEM THIS LONG
WITH ALL THAT HELP?
WOW, WHAT A BUNCH OF LOSERS.
WHAT IS TAKARA ANYWAY?
[GASPS]
WHAT'S WRONG?
OW.
HANG ON. IS THIS IT?
EVERYONE'S BACK?
SO NONE OF YOU GAVE UP?
THEN WHO SET OFF
THAT BOTTLE ROCKET?
OUCH.
SHIEMI?
WHOO-HOO!
IT'S THAT GUY
FROM THE AMUSEMENT PARK.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
- SHURA!
- [AMAIMON]
GO GET THEM, BEHEMOTH!
- [ROARS]
- IT TOOK HIM LONG ENOUGH.
- [WHISTLES]
- [GASPS]
A SNAKE!
[SHOUTS]
[ROARING]
[AMAIMON]
YAY!
[MEPHISTO LAUGHING]
I THOUGHT I COULD JUST SIT,
RELAX AND ENJOY THE FUN
WITH A NICE CUP OF TEA.
OH, WELL.
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
SHE'S QUITE FORMIDABLE,
ISN'T SHE?
[GROANS]
I'LL KILL HER.
YOU WON'T.
IF YOU KILL EVEN ONE OF THEM,
I'LL MOST DEFINITELY KILL YOU.
RIGHT. I'M SORRY, BROTHER.
I'LL BE MORE PATIENT.
AN ABSOLUTE BARRIER?
YEP. EVERYTHING INSIDE
THE MAGIC CIRCLE IS SAFE,
AND EVERYTHING OUTSIDE
IS REPELLED.
YOU GUYS SHOULD BE SAFE HERE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
THAT'S ALL GREAT,
BUT WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THAT GUY?
YEAH, MISS SHURA.
IS HE SUPPOSED TO BE
PART OF OUR TRAINING?
[SHIMA] AND DON'T YOU THINK
HE'S A LITTLE TOO TOUGH
FOR US TO HANDLE?
TRAINING'S OVER FOR TODAY.
WE HAVE TO GET READY
FOR AMAIMON'S NEXT ATTACK.
[ALL]
AMAIMON?
[KAMIKI]
DO YOU MEAN ONE OF
THE EIGHT KINGS? THE BAAL?
THE KING OF EARTH?
THAT AMAIMON?
UH-HUH. AND SINCE HE'S
ONE OF THE BIG GUNS,
YOU EXWIRES DON'T STAND
MUCH OF A CHANCE ON YOUR OWN
AGAINST HIM.
EVERYONE GATHER AROUND.
I'M GONNA GIVE YOU GUYS...
A DOSE OF SOME TRIPLE-C
CONCENTRATED HOLY WATER.
BUT WHY--
[SPLUTTERS]
DOES HE WANNA FIGHT US?
YEAH, THIS HAS GOTTA BE
SOME KIND OF--
KIND OF JOKE.
[GASPS]
WHOOPS.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
IT WOULD'VE GOTTEN UGLY...
IF I ENDED UP
POURING SOME ON YOU.
[SHURA]
IN THE BEGINNING, GOD CREATED
HEAVEN AND THE EARTH.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS ARE GOOD
UNTIL THE HOLY WATER DRIES.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
THE DAMAGE SHOULDN'T BE
TOO BAD.
WHAT ABOUT OKUMURA?
AREN'T YOU GONNA
SPLASH HIM WITH SOME?
YEAH.
HE'S SORT OF ALLERGIC
TO HOLY WATER, SO--
ALLERGIC TO HOLY WATER?
I NEVER HEARD THAT ONE BEFORE.
UH, WAIT.
HAS ANYONE SEEN YUKIO?
HE WAS SORT OF GETTING
IN THE WAY,
SO I SENT HIM OFF SOMEWHERE.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[GROWLING]
[YUKIO THINKING]
SOMETHING'S WRONG HERE.
THESE CHUCHI WERE RAISED
BY TAMERS, SO WHY ARE
THEY ATTACKING US?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[LINE RINGING]
WHAT THE HELL?
I CAN'T GET THROUGH TO ANY
OF OUR EMERGENCY CONTACTS.
AND I CAN'T REACH
ANY OF OUR TEACHERS EITHER.
AMAIMON'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A BIG SHOT, SO WHAT'S
HE PICKING ON US FOR?
DUNNO. I'M WONDERING
THE SAME THING.
HEY.
HMM?
I DON'T KNOW THE REASON
WHY HE'S DOING IT, BUT I THINK
I KNOW WHO HE'S AFTER.
- IT'S ME.
- YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
THE BARRIER'S STRONG ENOUGH,
SO EVEN SOMEONE
LIKE AMAIMON'S...
GONNA HAVE A TOUGH TIME
GETTING THROUGH,
BUT THIS TIME
SOMETHING'S DIFFERENT.
I CAN'T SHAKE THE FEELING
THAT HE'S PLANNING SOMETHING.
ANYWAY, IF HE TRIES
TO COME AFTER YOU AGAIN,
YOU'D BETTER TAKE THE KOMA SWORD
AND GET THE HELL AWAY FROM HERE.
THE KOMA SWORD?
FROM HERE IT DESCENDS,
AND TO HIM IT SHALL RETURN.
GO ON.
TAKE IT.
UH, I--
OH, COME ON.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU WANTED IT SO BAD.
HERE IT IS.
HOLD ON! YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T WANT ME USING
MY POWER IN FRONT OF ANYONE.
"DON'T BE FLAMING UP," REMEMBER?
SHUT YOUR TRAP, KID.
YOU SPARKED UP
EVEN AFTER I WARNED YOU.
YOU CAN'T HIDE
ANYTHING FROM ME.
[GROANS]
[LAUGHS]
ANYCRAP, IF YOU'RE GONNA PUT
THE HURT ON SOMEONE,
HOW DO YOU EXPECT TO DO THAT
WITHOUT YOUR FLAMES?
I GUESS I--
AMAIMON'S THE KING
OF EARTH, PAL.
HE AIN'T NO BOTTOM FEEDER.
STOP THINKING ABOUT IT.
TAKE IT.
[SHIMA]
M-MORIYAMA?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[BOTH GASP]
NO!
SHIEMI?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
SOMEBODY STOP HER!
[SQUISHING]
[SHURA]
WHAT THE HELL?
THAT'S A PARASITE.
SHIEMI!
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO THAT GIRL?
OH, I JUST HAD A FEMALE CHUCHI
LAY AN EGG INSIDE HER,
THAT'S ALL.
IT TOOK FOREVER AND A HALF
FOR IT TO HATCH,
BUT NOW THAT IT'S NIBBLING
ON HER NERVOUS SYSTEM,
THIS YOUNG LADY WILL DO
WHATEVER I TELL HER TO.
- [GROWLS]
- JUMP!
GET BACK HERE, CONE HEAD!
HEY, YOU IDIOT.
COME BACK HERE!
[ROARING]
[GASPS]
[SNARLING]
[ROARS]
[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
NO!
[GROANS]
GO GET HIM.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
MM.
OKUMURA!
NOBODY LEAVES
THE MAGIC CIRCLE...
FOR ANY REASON,
YOU GOT THAT?
BUT--
[THINKING]
THAT IDIOT. NOT AGAIN.
COME BACK HERE, DAMN IT!
[GRUNTING]
WHAT DO YOU WANT, YOU BASTARD?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
TO SHIEMI?
GOOD QUESTION.
HMM.
I KNOW. I'M GOING TO MAKE
THIS PRETTY YOUNG THING MY WIFE.
HUH?
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
WILL YOU BE MINE,
TO HAVE AND TO HOLD?
WILL YOU HONOR ME
AND CHERISH ME
IN SICKNESS AND HEALTH?
TILL DEATH DO US PART
AND STUFF?
AND WILL YOU LOVE ME
FOREVER AND EVER
UNTIL THE DAY YOU DIE?
TO SEAL OUR VOW OF ETERNAL LOVE,
I WILL NOW BITE YOUR LIPS OFF.
[GROWLS]
KNOCK IT OFF!
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I WAS GONNA SAY THE SAME THING.
- [RIN SHOUTING]
- [ALL GASPING]
CUT THE KID SOME SLACK,
YOU ASSHOLE!
[SHOUTING]
AW, COME ON.
WHY DON'T YOU DRAW
YOUR SWORD?
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULDN'T
TEASE ME LIKE THIS.
THAT GODDAMN SON OF A--
NO! BON, STOP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE THE CIRCLE.
[GRUNTS]
BON, TRY TO CALM DOWN,
OKAY?
[HUFFS]
CALM DOWN, MY ASS.
FEED THAT SHIT TO THE DOGS.
RIGHT NOW I'M SO PISSED OFF
AT THAT PUNK,
I COULD FRIGGIN' EXPLODE.
[BOTH GRUNT]
[GROANS]
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
[MIWA]
SHIMA, WAIT!
UH--
[GRUNTS]
HUH? ARE YOU KIDDING?
COME BACK!
YOU'RE GOING
TO GET KILLED!
UNBELIEVABLE.
THEY'RE CRAZY.
I'M SO OVER THIS.
HUH?
YOO-HOO!
EXCUSE ME, BUT I THOUGHT
THIS GIRL WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE IMPORTANT TO YOU.
IF SHE IS, WHY AREN'T YOU
GOING FOR THE KILL?
[GROANING]
GO TO HELL.
HMM. OH, WELL.
I SUPPOSE I DON'T HAVE
ANY USE FOR HER NOW.
BUT SINCE SHE'S HERE,
MAYBE I'LL HAVE
ONE OF HER EYEBALLS.
- [GRUNTS]
- A COUSIN OF MINE HAS
A PENCHANT FOR THE OCCULT,
AND I PROMISED TO PICK UP
A FEW FOR HIS COLLECTION.
- I'M GONNA--
- [BOTTLE ROCKET WHISTLES]
[EXPLOSION]
HUH?
YOU FORGOT TO INVITE US
TO THE PARTY,
SO WE'RE CRASHING IT.
NO! GET AWAY!
RUN FOR IT, OKUMURA.
WE'LL KEEP HIM BUSY.
UH, I--
I-I'M JUST HERE
TO SAVE MORIYAMA.
SO-- SO YEAH.
DO WHAT I SAID-- RUN!
[FIZZLING]
[GASPING]
[WHISTLING]
[SCREAMS]
UH-OH.
WHAT THE HELL?
YOU HIT MORIYAMA.
HUH?
[ALL]
UH--
- [GASPS]
- [LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
BROCCOLI.
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
[SUGURO]
SHIMA!
[MIWA] SHIMA!
NEKO!
[SCREAMING]
KONEKOMARU--
[GASPS]
[BOTH GROANING]
YOU LAUGHED AT ME,
DIDN'T YOU?
[GROANS]
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT YOU, WEIRDO.
THE GUY I'M SUPER PISSED AT
IS HIM.
YA HEAR THAT, OKUMURA?
YOU ACT LIKE YOU DON'T CARE,
BUT THEN YOU HELP SOMEONE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE A LOSER,
AND THEN YOU GO KICK
ALL KINDS OF ASS.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU??
WHY DO YOU GO AROUND
ACTING LIKE A HE--
[GROANS]
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
- DON'T IGNORE ME.
- STOP!
[THINKING]
YOU GUYS--
[MIWA]
IF YOU'RE GONNA TAKE SATAN ON,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA NEED SOME HELP.
[SHIMA]
I'M A WIMP,
BUT I GOT YOUR BACK.
[SHIEMI]
RIN, WE'RE HERE FOR YOU.
[SUGURO]
YOU'VE GOT FRIENDS.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
[THINKING]
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
YOU'VE ALL BEEN SO GOOD TO ME.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
RIN! IT'S A TRAP!
DON'T FALL FOR IT.
[PANTING]
YUKIO, I'M SORRY.
I-- I GUESS I JUST DON'T GOT IT
IN ME TO KEEP LYING TO EVERYONE,
SO I DECIDED...
I WANT TO USE MY POWER
TO DO SOMETHING GOOD...
FOR EVERYONE!
[GROANING]
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[LAUGHING]
[PANTING, GASPS]
WELL? YOU WANT ME, HERE I AM!
YAY!
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTING]
HOLY CRAP.
I-IS OKUMURA...
WHAT I THINK HE IS?
THE SWORD.
HUH?
KURIKARA.
[SHOUTING]
[LAUGHING]
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
[SHOUTING]
- [RIN SHOUTING]
- [AMAIMON SCREAMING]
BURN IN HELL, BASTARD!
[SHOUTING]
[MEPHISTO LAUGHING]
NOTHING'S MORE VULNERABLE
THAN A DEMON'S TAIL.
A GENTLEMAN KNOWS
HOW TO KEEP IT TUCKED IN TIGHT.
THERE'S SO MUCH
YOU STILL NEED TO LEARN.
STARTING WITH YOUR DESIRES,
MY BOY.
[SHOUTING]
GOT IT.
HEY, IS EVERYONE OKAY?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
ALL THIS TIME?
WELL, I WASN'T
FARTING AROUND,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
I WAS FIGHTING
AMAIMON'S PET.
WE GOTTA BAIL NOW.
IT'S NOT SAFE HERE.
[GASPS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
[SHURA, THINKING]
AND YOU WANTED ME
TO BABY-SIT THAT MONSTER.
DAMN YOU, SHIRO.
AT LEAST I'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
ON ONE SIDE OF THE PATH
ARE DEMONS, PLEASURE SEEKERS--
INCAPABLE OF ANYTHING
BUT DESTRUCTION.
ON THE OTHER ARE HUMANS,
WHOSE VAGUE MORALITY
MAKES THEM WEAK.
I WONDER...
WHICH PATH WILL YOU CHOOSE?
[BOTH SHOUTING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[GRUNTING]
[SWORD RINGING]
HUH?
IS THAT RIN?
[AMAIMON]
UNBELIEVABLE POWER.
JUST LIKE FATHER'S.
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[RIN SHOUTING]
[CRACKS]
[ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
GOOD SHOW.
I NEVER IMAGINED HE'D OVERWHELM
AMAIMON SO COMPLETELY.
[GASPING]
[MEPHISTO]
YOU'VE FOUGHT ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
TIME FOR A GOOD LONG REST.
EINS, ZWEI, DREI.
KUCHEN KUCKUCKS UHR.
- [CHIMING]
- [CUCKOOING]
HUH?
[CUCKOOS]
[AMAIMON SCREAMING]
[SIGHS]
NOW THEN--
[SHOUTING]
[GASPING]
[GROWLING]
THE LAD'S BEEN CONSUMED
BY HIS FLAMES.
[SNARLING]
MY, MY.
YOU'RE SUCH A HANDFUL,
LITTLE BROTHER.
[SNARLING]
[METAL CRACKS]
♪ [WOMAN SINGING
IN JAPANESE]
[MAN #1]
AH, SO BLUE.
AS BLUE AS IT WAS
THAT NIGHT, NO?
[MAN #2]
IS THIS CREATURE I SEE
BEFORE ME THE SON OF SATAN?
[MEPHISTO]
THAT HE IS, YOUR HONOR.
[MAN #1]
I SHALL EXECUTE
THE SPAWN OF SATAN.