[straining]
I got it!
[priest] It's gonna burst!
[chanting]
Hah!
Oh, no!
[groaning]
Eww, that's rank!
I think I see it!
The Impure King's heart!
[straining]
[Rin] Suguro! Suguro!
Are you OK over there?!
[gagging]
Suguro! [straining]
Shit!
[groaning]
[gasps]
[gagging]
Suguro!
It seems the plot has taken
a most dramatic turn.
An enemy resurrected.
The life of a dear friend
hanging in the balance.
The tension is unbearable.
What will you do now,
little brother?
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyou" in Japanese]
[shouting]
[coughing]
Yaa! I need a doctor!
The miasma is too thick!
Try to hold out!
[Shura] Director!
Look, the flame barrier
is keeping the miasma contained.
We should get outta here
and find a plan to deal with it.
We have no choice. Retreat!
All teams regroup
outside the barrier!
Holy crap.
Is that it, the Impure King?
Hah! So the big boss
is finally here.
Come on, you scumbag!
I'm Kinzo Shima, and I'd rather
die standing my ground
than run away from‐‐
Idiot, I gave you an order!
So move it!
Hurry, everyone!
Get out of the barrier now!
[Todo sighs]
Now then, where was I?
Oh, this is interesting.
[chuckles]
It seems you're under Ucchusma's
protection, Mr. Shima.
Clever.
He tore you up pretty good.
Get out of here.
[Yukio] No, I can still fight.
[Yukio thinking] I wonder if
anyone else noticed my eyes.
What happened to them?
[Todo] So here we are.
Your Agni versus my Karura.
I'm curious to find out
which is stronger.
Why don't we have
a test of strength to see?
I'm gonna vaporize you.
Really?
[intones chant]
‐[Todo chuckles]
‐[all gasp]
He absorbed them.
Yaaa!
Down here!
[strains]
[gasps]
[Todo] Mr. Shima?
Don't you remember anything
I taught you back
at the academy?
According to the table
of demonic elements,
when two similar
elements collide,
the stronger always absorbs
the weaker.
And in our case,
Karura's ability to regenerate
is so effective,
it's almost unfair.
As far as strength goes, I win.
Karura.
That explains everything.
He's possessed by the Phoenix.
I have nothing to gain playing
around with you anymore.
Goodbye, gentlemen.
[priests groaning]
We're dealing
with an upper‐level demon
that can absorb our flames
to strengthen itself.
I hate to say this, but
it's got us at a disadvantage.
Let's fall back and regroup.
[Yukio] Excuse me.
I have an idea,
but it's dangerous.
All right, let's hear it.
[Todo] It's a little late
for strategy meetings,
I'm afraid.
You're right,
that's dangerous and crazy.
I know, but if we don't...
[priest groans]
[priest] Minami!
Hmm. Remember me?
We'll die either way if we
don't try, so let's do it.
All right, we're with you.
Narumi and Shishamo,
take point.
[both] Right!
Kumagai and Chigusa, I need you
to reinforce my flames.
[both] Right!
[reciting chant]
[Todo] Come on then.
I'm dying to know what you boys
were scheming about.
[attackers straining]
[Todo chuckles]
[chuckles]
[Todo] Don't you people
pay any attention?
Your flame attacks
are like food to me.
And I'm eating it all up!
Scratch that.
It's more like dessert,
and I do love dessert.
Huh?
‐[groaning]
‐Bastard!
[reciting chant]
[Todo] Honestly, what do I have
to do to make you understand?
A person must think things
all the way through
before they act.
You should work
on that short fuse of yours.
You were that way in class, too.
Think, boy,
you'll have better ideas.
Nope. This wasn't my idea.
It was Mister Four‐Eyes there.
[Todo] What?
[Yukio] A demon
and the body it possesses
must have equivalent natures.
The more flame Todo absorbs,
the less his mortal body
will be able to contain them.
What's happening to me?
The end result: overload.
[gasping]
Todo said he switched demons.
If the one he's using now
is Karura,
the Phoenix,
his body will be so burned,
it will turn to ash.
[Todo] Oh, I get it.
You boys were trying to make me
overheat with that assault.
Well, I guess the lesson here
is to not overindulge
in dessert.
See, I learned something
after all.
But you're still underestimating
Karura's ability to heal me.
‐[body crackles]
‐Huh?
I see.
It's raining.
[Yukio] Your body's immortal,
but if it's turned to ash
and water hits it,
it won't be able
to regenerate so easily.
I guess you win after all.
I can't believe...
thiiiiiis...
‐[sighs]
‐[Juzo] Is he dead now?
No, this will only
buy us some time.
We have to scoop up what's left
of him in separate containers
and put seals on them.
‐If not, he'll regenerate.
‐Great.
Chigusa, Kumagai!
Take Minami and the others
over to the main group.
‐Tell them I need some backup.
‐Right.
‐And how about you?
‐I'll be... fine.
[groans] Get going!
[coughing]
Let me have a look.
‐I said I'm fine.
‐Hardly.
[Yukio thinking] I can't relax
until Todo's contained.
Then I'll ask him what he knows
about the Impure King.
[Todo] Oh, Mr. Okumura.
[gasps]
[groaning]
Todo!
Where are you?
Where?!
[murmuring]
[coughing]
[Yukio] Did everyone make it?
[Uwabami] I hope so.
A person can't last
with the amount of miasma
trapped in the barrier.
It went up just in time
and prevented God knows
how many deaths.
But who could have cast
such a high‐level spell?
It's obvious, the Master did.
[Konekomaru] It wasn't!
[Uwabami] Konekomaru! Renzo!
The Master didn't put it up.
Bon cast the spell
that created the barrier.
Okumura went with him and
both of them are still inside!
[gasps] Are you sure?
Super sure. The Master's hurt
and Kamiki and Moriyama
are with him.
They're on the eastern slope.
Master Yaozo, please,
our friends need help!
All rightie.
I'll go on ahead,
slip inside the barrier
and help Suguro and Okumura.
[Yaozo] Right. We'll talk
to the boys and find out
what they know.
Then I'll send up teams
to assist you and the Master.
[Shura] Awesome.
[boys gasp]
[Shura] Miwa, Shima,
you did good.
Man, I deserve more than
a lame pat on the head.
I could use some nuzzlin'
after what I went through.
Back to normal, huh?
[Shura] Rin, I hope you got
your confidence back.
[Izumo groaning]
It's a fungus demon,
so we should use ferns and moss.
Hey, Nee, I need libby...
I meant liverwort
and hornwort.
Cover the fungus with those.
[Nee] Yaaaa!
[Nee casting spell]
[Shiemi] Skeleton fork next!
Then horsetail!
Then adder's tongue!
[Izumo thinking]
Wow! She's really pushing
her familiar.
How can she handle it?
[groaning]
Suguro!
[Suguro groaning]
Karura!
I call for your protection!
[Karura] As you wish.
I managed to drive away
the Impure King.
However, you have cast
a double spell
and it will quickly deplete
your energy.
[coughing]
[footsteps]
[Rin] Suguro! You OK?!
‐[Kuro mews]
‐[Rin] What did you do?
[Karura] I diverted a small bit
of power from the barrier
to protect Ryuji.
If the caster loses
consciousness, all is lost.
The Impure King is drawn
to the energy of the living.
But against fire,
he is weakened.
This should keep him away
for the time being.
‐Great, so now we just‐‐
‐[Suguro] Hang on.
[Suguro] I doubt the barrier
will hold another 15 minutes.
Say what? What do you mean?
Dude, I'm totally
wiped out here.
I feel like I hit
the freakin' wall.
I don't think I could
do this for much longer.
I guess Koneko and Shima
couldn't get to the others yet.
I hope whatever happens...
that they're OK.
Sure they are, they gotta be!
[gasps]
[creature roaring]
Rin!
‐[Kuro yowls]
‐Kuro! Don't! Leave it alone!
[Impure King groans]
‐[Kuro yowls]
‐Kuro!
That does it!
I'm gonna...
[straining]
[gasps] Damn it!
I made it all the way here
and I still can't draw it.
Why can't I draw it?!
[straining]
[panting]
Well... I guess this is it.
I can hold the barrier
for a bit longer...
so get out while you can.
No!
[Suguro] Go on.
You need to evacuate
as many people as you can.
Hurry up. Don't argue.
Every second counts now.
Go!
‐Wait, that's right!
‐[Suguro] Huh?
[Rin] What's that thing called?
Kyoto something.
Oh, now I remember.
Kyoto Tower!
Uh...
Dude, I wanna go see it
and go to the top.
Can we go, like maybe tomorrow?
You're from here,
and I want a tour.
I read it's a tower
but with a bath house in it.
I so gotta see that.
It'd be rad if we could get
everyone to go too.
Thing is, it'd suck if Kyoto
and the tower got destroyed.
And if our friends died too...
that'd suck worse.
We'll win.
We gotta.
Why...
Why the hell are you nerding out
about Kyoto freakin' Tower?!
‐[gasps]
‐With everything going on around
us, that's the place you pick?
Hell, I grew up here
and I've never been to it!
‐You're kidding!
‐Kyoto's got a ton
of famous temples
with historic relevance!
I don't know anything about
towers and "rally‐fences."
I, uh, just thought
the tower was cool.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[chuckling]
[Suguro thinking] Oh, man,
he's scared and trying
to cheer me up.
Are you... OK down there?
[Suguro] Yeah.
Whatever.
I give up, you win.
Even though I know you're
B. S.'ing, I'm up for it.
We're friends, after all.
Okumura, I trust you.
[Impure King roaring]
[Rin thinking] Old man... why
did you ever bother saving me?
I'm useless.
So, what was the point
in saving someone like me,
if I can't help now?
Then what the hell...
did you save my life for?!
[Suguro] Okumura!
Rin!
[Suguro] He did it.
He drew the sword!
[Rin snarling]
[Impure King groaning]
[Suguro] Okumura!
[snarls]
[Rin Akatsuki singing
"Kono Te De" in Japanese]
[Mephisto]
Yes! Gaze into the abyss!