[Tatsuma, feebly] Wait.
Please, Rin.
I'm begging you.
Use the Koma Sword
and destroy the Impure King.
I know I'm just
a stranger to you
and what I'm asking
is beyond crazy, but still...
if you have even...
[Yukio] "...the tiniest sliver
of compassion in you,
like your father had in him,
I hope you'll
accept my request.
Thank you for taking
the time to read this.
Tatsuma Suguro."
[chuckles]
That letter turned out
to be a bigger eye‐opener
than I thought.
You said it, but we can't
give Rin the Koma Sword.
Combined with his flames,
who knows how they'll affect
the Impure King?
I hate to disappoint
Suguro's dad, but this is
too risky for us to...
The letter's addressed to you,
Rin, so it's your decision.
What do you want to do?
I wanna...
Really? What's the point
in asking him?
[Rin] I... I wanna help.
Come on! Do you even understand
the mess you're in?
I wanna help 'cause our old man
saved my life.
So like, if there's a chance
I can save someone else,
I can't sit and do nothing.
Hell, I know I screwed up.
I just wanna help.
‐Well, you can't and that's‐‐
‐[Shura] Ah, screw it.
[Shura] From here it descends
and to him it shall return.
‐What do you think you're doing?
‐Hmm? What do you mean?
If he wants to help,
we need to make sure
he can draw this thing
and still keep his cool.
So, let's see if he can.
‐Uh...
‐No! Have you gone
completely insane?
He's here because he just
lost control, and now you want
to hand him the sword
and hope for the best?!
If he flares up again,
he's gonna be executed for sure!
Listen, Doofus!
The Vatican knew
what was going down
when I started chanting
the imprisonment spell,
so they could have executed Rin
whenever they felt like
after that, but they didn't!
The kid's already screwed,
so there's no point
in pussy‐footing around now!
Besides, if the Impure King
really has come back to life,
don't you think that
son of a bitch is a bigger
threat to the world
than Rin is?! [straining]
You know what he can do
when he's all riled up.
You've seen his flames work
against demons before!
I say it's worth a shot.
Go ahead, try and draw it.
[straining]
Huh?
What's wrong?
[Yukio] What are you doing, Rin?
[Rin, straining] It's, uh...
What's with this thing?
I can't draw it!
‐Huh?
‐Would you quit screwing around?
I'm not, damn it!
Arrgh! I don't know why,
but it ain't budging.
All right then, let me take
a crack at that thing.
Come on, gimme.
What? No, I can do it.
It's just a little stuck is all.
‐Just need to pull
a little harder.
‐Please don't break it.
Oh, I got it.
You're scared, ain't ya?
‐Uh...
‐[Shura] I can't say
I blame ya.
A little while ago,
you were up on that roof,
stoked you got control
of your flames,
and then you flared up.
I bet you feel like you're back
to square one now, huh?
You're thinking,
"What's gonna happen to me
if I draw the sword?
Am I gonna be OK or am I
gonna lose control again?
And what if this time I really
hurt someone I care about?"
‐[Rin] No, I...
‐[Shura] You know I'm right.
[Shura] You can't draw it
'cause you lost your confidence.
[Rin] Huh?
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyou" in Japanese]
Hang on a sec.
Not having confidence is why
I can't draw this thing?
Come on, you tried.
Now give the sword back.
[Rin straining]
[Mephisto] Goodness gracious.
Alley‐oop.
Guten abend,
my little trouble makers.
[chuckles]
‐[Yukio] Sir Pheles?
‐Mephisto. What do you want?
Your rude tone is as
disappointing as this venue.
To think, my first
grand appearance in ages
and it's in a jail...
an icky jail.
Rejoice, though, for I have
arrived to clean up your mess.
Eins, zwei und drei!
Das staärkste Gefaängnis.
The most impenetrable prison.
[Rin gasps]
[groans]
I just received word
from the Vatican.
Apparently,
due to Rin's bad behavior,
the Inquest Committee headed
by the Grigori took a vote.
Rin Okumura, you've been
sentenced to death.
[Rin groans]
[Rin] No! Wait!
[gears whirring]
I can't believe
they decided so fast.
[Mephisto] You think I'm lying?
Please. I'm far too busy
to play around like that.
[Shura] Yukio, you OK?
Regardless of the boy's fate,
destroying the Impure King
is our top priority.
[sneezes]
Excuse me.
Be a dear and hold this.
Back up a second there.
If you know about
the Impure King,
why don't you help?
‐Surely you're joking.
‐[snaps fingers]
Unfortunately, I can't abide
fungus‐y things
due to my allergies.
‐My poor nose!
‐[Shura] Oh, my God.
If it's been revived,
the Impure King
will grow rapidly.
As soon as it reaches maturity,
Kyoto will become a city
of death.
I'm on my way back
to the field office
with Mamushi.
Get everyone together
and meet us at the entrance.
Can you see it from there yet?
Uwabami, can you see it?
[Uwabami] Yes, I...
I think so.
Defeating the Impure King
will most likely take
a great deal of manpower.
And I'd like to do my part.
Please accept this equipment
as my gift.
They're nothing fancy,
but I think you'll find them
very helpful.
‐Huh?
‐And now I must depart.
Best of luck, kiddies.
[Shura] Hey, wait!
Man, what a bastard.
Let's just focus on doing
what we can.
‐What, for Rin?
‐No, the Impure King.
The Myoda is gonna need
our help destroying it.
[Shura groans]
The field office just sent
an emergency summons.
They need anyone who's able
over there!
‐Yes, sir!
‐Hurry!
[Renzo] I wonder what's going on
with all the commotion
out there.
[Konekomaru] It sounds like
something serious.
[priest] Hey, is it true
they caught Mamushi?
[priest 2] Yeah, Juzo did.
He's bringing her back.
Mamushi?
[Konekomaru] Bon!
[priest] Look, Juzo's back!
[Uwabami] Mamushi! Juzo!
[Mamushi] Thank you all
for coming so I can...
[Mamushi coughs]
...so I can try
to redeem myself.
First I... [coughs]
I... I admit I am the traitor.
Even so, put your feelings
about that aside
and listen to me.
As most of you already know,
Saburota Todo and I stole
the Right and Left Eyes.
A little while ago, we used them
to revive the Impure King.
[priest] That's impossible!
But the Impure King was defeated
way back in the Edo period.
[Mamushi] Its body has been kept
in a state of suspended
animation
beneath Kongo‐Shinzan.
‐[worried murmurs]
‐Hey, cut the chatter!
Right now, it's on the loose
and growing.
Master Tatsuma's up there, too.
He's taking that demon on
all by himself.
I beg you, please send help.
He can't fight the Impure King
on his own!
‐You've got some nerve!
‐You brought it back to life,
so you deal with it.
We don't even know
what we're dealing with.
Yeah, we don't know how
to fight it.
This is not the time
to be arguing amongst ourselves.
Every exorcist, including
security teams one and two
and the team from the keep,
will deploy to assist
the Master.
The Impure King is related
to the King of Rot.
So to counter the miasma,
you'll need to get vaccinated.
[priest] Hurry!
Get the syringes ready.
[priest 2] On it!
‐[Mamushi coughing]
‐[Suguro] Mamushi!
M‐Master Ryuji!
Your eye. I'll get the doc.
I'm sorry.
He's alone.
The Master's alone!
Save him!
[Juzo] Don't worry, Bon,
I'll get her to the infirmary.
Then what? You going?
Yeah, of course.
I'll head up as soon as
I got her settled.
As for you and your pals,
you'd better head back
to the inn for now.
Keep him safe!
Anything happens to him,
you're dead, got it,
Renzo, Koneko?!
Yeah, we got it.
He's safe with us.
Forget about me.
[coughs]
Hurry and help the Master...
[Juzo] Shut up.
I'll get you for this, Todo!
[Renzo] There's nothing
we can do, Bon.
You heard what my bro said.
We have to go back to the inn.
Yo, you guys,
come here for a sec.
‐I've got something for you.
‐Ma'am, how is Rin?
The top brass heard about
his flare‐up and they just
sentenced him to death.
[Shiemi and Suguro gasp]
That's an order from the Vatican
and it can't be overturned
by anyone.
Any crap...
Here you go, Suguro.
I'm trusting you
with this thing.
Kurikara!
[Shura] Oh, and here's a letter
your dad wrote to Rin.
It says we're gonna need
his power to destroy
the Impure King.
Rin did say he's down to fight.
But first he's gonna need you
to bust him out.
The only way he'll get
a pardon now is if he does
something big and heroic.
Here, these are camo‐panchos.
Put 'em on and you'll be
invisible.
You can walk right up
to his cell
and no one's gonna notice
you're there.
Ms. Kirigakure, it's time to go.
OK!
As you see, the Order's
got me on a tight leash
so I got to behave.
You have to figure it out
from here.
I'm counting on you.
Let's go, guys.
Rin needs our help!
Hell, I wanna get him out
of there as much as anyone.
The thing is, we don't wanna
piss off the Vatican.
But... this is our one
and only chance to save Rin.
If we don't try,
we'll regret it.
Cell block's down this way.
‐Bon!
‐Thank you, Suguro.
‐Are you cool with this, Koneko?
‐Thanks, Miwa!
[Konekomaru] We promised
we'd protect Bon.
Besides, she's right.
I would regret it.
What the...
Dude, we'd better do
what Juzo said.
‐Y‐You're going, too?!
‐Thanks, Kamiki!
What's gotten into everyone?
They're all gonna d‐‐
Move your ass, Renzo!
While you kids are back
at the inn taking a nap,
I'll be spilling my blood
for Myoda!
[hysterical laughter]
Everyone's nuts.
All this stuff
about Myoda and regret.
I just don't get
what all the fuss is about.
Ah, jeez, damn it!
I hate my life!
‐Ow!
‐Look, for the last time,
no talking.
‐I didn't. I thought it was you.
‐I didn't say anything.
‐Quit messing around.
‐I'm not.
[guard] Jeez!
That was way too close.
[Renzo, whispering] Thanks for
stepping on my heel, Koneko.
[Konekomaru] I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to.
[Izumo] The only problem
with these panchos
is we can't see each other.
Other than that,
they're pretty cool.
[Suguro] Shh!
His cell's coming up.
That's a weird looking door.
[Gefaängnis] Wee‐ooh,
wee‐ooh, wee‐ooh, wee‐ooh!
[chuckles]
I am Das Staärkste Gefaängnis,
the impenetrable prison.
I can't be unlocked
from the inside
but I can be opened easily
from the outside.
See if you can answer my riddle!
‐What the heck is this thing?
‐A demon!
[Gefaängnis] And the riddle is,
what makes me so impenetrable?
Try to break into me
and see for yourselves.
‐I guess we've got no choice.
‐Huh!
[Gefaängnis giggles]
The answer is:
I am impenetrable because I can
freeze those who come at me
with hostile intent
in their tracks.
Now you know how
I got my name. [giggles]
Oh, my gosh. Hey, wait.
Um, sir, how come
you didn't freeze me, too?
Because you pose no threat
to me.
You're weak
and carry no weapons.
[chuckles]
[Shiemi, thinking]
He's right.
Without Nee's help,
I am weak.
Still, I can't let Rin die.
I won't let that happen!
You said you can be opened
from the outside.
[Gefaängnis] Indeed.
You can get in,
but you can't get out.
[Shiemi, thinking]
Everyone needs him.
I have to try.
[door creaks open]
What the hell?
Where am I?
I'm not dying here.
No way am I gonna die
in this shit hole!
[metal clangs]
I can't die.
Or maybe I should.
[Mephisto] We could kill you,
or you could try
to kill us and run.
Or you could also kill
yourself: three options.
[Yukio] You should just die!
[Rin, thinking] My pop
saved my life for a reason.
The last thing I want
is to waste it.
But, in the end...
[Shura] You're thinking,
"What's gonna happen to me
if I draw the sword,
and what if this time I really
hurt someone I care about?"
[Rin, thinking] Maybe it's
better for everyone
if I was gone.
But...
then I'll die
without helping anyone
and without making things right
with the folks I care about.
So why did I even
get a second chance?
Old man, why did you save me?
What was the point?
[Shiemi panting]
[Shiemi] Rin!
Shiemi?
I came to get you!
[panting]
We talked to Ms. Kirigakure.
She told us what you said.
Everyone's waiting out there
and we all wanna help you.
So come on,
let's get out of here!
Stay away from me.
What do you mean, why?
[Rin] Simple. I can't control
my flames without confidence.
I thought,
if I just stuck with it,
I'd get the hang of it
at some point.
But now I know
that's never going to happen.
That's just the way it is.
Maybe I'd be
better off if I died.
What are you saying?
Are you crazy?!
How could you say such a thing?
Trust me,
you wouldn't understand.
It's not something you need to,
anyway.
Stop it! Don't say that!
You can't just laugh
and push me away!
I'm on your side!
I'm here because
I wanna help you!
Don't you get it?
I'm a monster! Go home!
[Shiemi thinking]
Huh? You're not hot.
You're warm.
I'm such a... dummy.
I was so focused
on my problems,
I never considered
what he was going through.
What...
What kind of friend am I?
Rin!
I'm sorry.
[Rin] Don't.
You're gonna get burned.
It's not safe.
I couldn't be safer.
Look, there's not
a single burn anywhere on me.
You made sure of that.
Don't you see, you did it!
[Rin] Uhh! B‐B‐But I'm still
a monster, you should be scared!
Huh? I'm not scared of you.
‐You sure?
‐Mm‐hmm.
[Rin roaring]
[door shattering]
It's Okumura!
No way, you really came
to save me!
Yeah. I mean, I wouldn't
like it if you died.
If it turns out you're not
dangerous, I'd like to be
friends with you.
Konekomaru.
Um, FYI, I'm here 'cause
Ms. Kirigakure told me to,
not for anything sappy.
Oh, um, I didn't wanna come,
but I did, so
you're welcome, dude.
You guys are... [sniffs]
Thanks for having my back.
[Shiemi screams]
[Rin] S‐Suguro!
I wasn't thinking straight
before, man.
I was kind of pissed
at my dad and stuff.
Anyway, you were right.
About my dad,
not, you know, the other crap.
You'll need this
if you're gonna fight.
Here, take it.
I, I'm sorry
I punched you in the face.
Yeah, well, I'll show you
the way to Kongo‐Shinzan.
After that, you can do
whatever you want.
I don't care.
I'll be fighting too
for what it's worth.
Suguro, I just want you
to trust me.
I can't help it
if I'm the spawn of Satan.
But I'll use my flames
for good, I swear!
Please! Have some faith in me.
[Suguro] I don't care
that you're Satan's kid.
The reason I'm pissed at you
is you were carrying
that baggage all by yourself.
If you'd have said something,
maybe we could have helped.
Why should I trust you
if you don't trust me?!
Am I the only one here
that thought we were friends?
No, wait, you got it all wrong!
You're pissed at him
'cause of that?
That's what's been bugging you?!
Huh? That's one for the books.
[Konekomaru] Shima!
[Rin thinking] Suguro.
I get it now.
OK, you're on.
It took ages,
but now the stage is set
and the cast is assembled.
The audience is settled in.
It's time to relax
and enjoy the show.
[explosion]
[Suguro] Guys, we're going
to Kongo‐Shinzan in Raku‐Hoku.
The Impure King's going down.
[Rin, thinking] This is
my chance to prove myself.
To everyone!
[Rin Akatsuki singing
"Kono Te De" in Japanese]
[Yukio] Becoming an Exorcist
was my choice!
Dad and Rin had nothing
to do with it!