[dog barking]
[clattering]
‐[man 1] This way!
‐[man 2] There he is,
corner him!
What are Exorcists doing here?
Did something happen?
This area is not safe, ma'am.
You should stay indoors
until we give the all‐clear.
[woman] Oh, uh, OK.
Come on, Satoru.
[Satoru] Aww, Mom!
I wanna see the Exorcist
fight the monsters!
‐[mother] Satoru!
‐No, wait, stay back!
‐[officer] Don't go down there,
you're in danger!
‐[boy screams]
‐[choking]
‐[mother] Satoru!
Damn it.
He's using the boy as a shield!
No, stand down!
Look, we've got you surrounded,
so let the boy go!
Hurting him
won't do you any good!
‐Wait! No, don't!
‐[boy whimpering]
[dramatic soundtrack plays]
[officer gasps]
[growling]
[Kuro]So pretty, so blue!
Aw, crap, it's too hard.
This sucks friggin' ass.
[Shura] Eh, you're the one
that sucks.
You're not improving at all.
[Rin] Eh... Shura!
[yawns] Morning, Rin.
[groans] How'd you find me?
Nobody knows about this place.
I knew you practiced up here
every morning since you started,
you booger.
[Rin] Wha... For real?
What did you expect?
It's my job to keep
an eye on you
because you're a threat
to the safety of everyone here,
including these poor candles.
You should only be lighting
the ones on the ends,
not nukin' 'em all,
you dumbass.
[Rin] I know, I know!
If your flames
get out of control again,
you'll be declared a demon
and executed, remember?
[Rin snarls]
Get a handle on using
those flames of yours.
You can't draw the Koma Sword
till you do.
[Rin groans]
[phone rings]
Yeah, I got it.
Come on, let's go.
Where?
[officer] Please, folks,
this area is dangerous.
For your safety,
I need you to stay back.
We'll be taking it from here.
[officer] Okumura,
right this way.
[Yukio]
I'm an Intermediate Exorcist.
First Class. Yukio Okumura.
Senior Ex, First Class,
Kirigakure.
‐Who's that?
‐[Rin snickers]
‐[Yukio] Huh?
‐[Rin] Me.
[Yukio] What are you
doing here, Rin?
I'm Rin Okumura,
Exorcist, ExWire, Ex‐cetera.
Here to kick demon ass.
Aren't you the...?
Is it OK he's here?
[Shura] Orders from
the Law Enforcement Division.
Besides, he ain't gonna
leave my sight.
Got him on a tight leash,
so you can bet your ass
he's gonna behave himself.
Can either of you tell us
what happened here?
‐Y‐yes, I can.
‐[Kinoshita] Take it easy.
I'm Saburota Todo.
My rank is Senior Exorcist,
Second Class,
and the Deep Keep's warden.
My job is to keep watch over
the Left Eye of the Impure King.
The academy had it sealed away
in the Keep, but it was stolen.
The Impure King?
‐Left eye? Like a real eye?
‐How the hell did that happen?
Hang on. I thought the Deep Keep
was supposed to be protected
by one of the strongest
magic barriers at the academy.
It is, but somehow the thief
got in and stole the eye anyway.
He wore a gas mask so
I couldn't tell who it was.
The Keep's elite guard and I
chased him to the alley.
We thought we had him cornered.
[officer] No, don't!
He used a boy as a shield
and then...
‐[whoosh!]
‐[officers groaning]
‐[Satoru] Mommy!
‐[mother] Satoru!
[Todo] He ran into that building
with the hostage,
but we haven't seen him
come out yet.
The miasma he released from
the flask is incredibly potent.
So far 31 people, including
civilians, have been infected,
and we don't have enough doctors
to help them all.
That boy was exposed to
the full force of the miasma,
and if he's not already dead,
he will be soon.
If the thief gets away
with the Left Eye, it's over.
This is the biggest failure
in True Cross's history!
[Rin] Dude, come on.
You know about
this Left Eye thing or...?
There's no time to panic.
We'll do everything we can
to get it back.
How tough is this guy
with the gas mask?
I have no idea, to be honest.
He never fought back,
he just ran.
We don't even know
if he's human or a demon.
‐Hmm.
‐We have to act, and fast.
Between Shura and I,
we'll figure out a way to‐‐
[woman] Excuse me.
Do you know if my son
is all right?
[sobs]
You don't have to worry
about a thing, lady.
The best in the biz is here
to do some head busting.
We'll get your kid back
safe and sound, promise.
If any...
We might be too late.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
He's been in there a long time,
so you should prepare
for the worst.
[sobbing]
What the hell, Yukio!
Shura, I'm leaving Rin
with you.
‐What?
‐That's cool.
I just remembered I got
something else I gotta do.
Come on, Rin, let's go.
[Rin] Screw you, man,
I'm comin'!
Exorcists are not superheroes.
We can't save everyone!
So don't go making promises!
You're writing that kid off
before you even do anything,
you chicken shit!
[Shura] All right, tough guy,
we got some errands to run.
Let go, Boobzilla!
[Rin grumbling]
[Yukio] That idiot.
‐[Todo] Okumura?
‐Huh?
‐[Yukio] Mr. Todo?
‐Let me go with you, please.
[Yukio] Are you sure
you're well enough?
[Todo] I've been inoculated.
I have to go.
This happened on my watch.
I understand, sir.
Then let's head in.
[canary singing]
[Todo] I hear your background
is... complicated.
But they say you're quite
talented for someone your age.
[Yukio] And I heard you come
from a long line
of well‐respected Exorcists.
Your family's been
guarding the Deep Keep
for generations now, hasn't it?
[Todo, wearily] It has.
[Rin] So, what's up
with this Left Eye thingie?
[Yukio] Huh? Rin?
Why are you here?
Where's Shura?
Who knows?
I gave her the slip.
What, you think you can
sideline me whenever things
get a little hairy?
I promised that kid's mom
we were gonna save him.
[canary singing]
I can carry the bird
if you want, I don't mind.
[Yukio] Fine, carry it.
But that's all, understand?
So, what's the bird for?
[Todo] It's a pseudo‐canary.
If it senses miasma,
it will stop chirping.
Then there must be some around
'cause it stopped chirping.
[Yukio gasps]
‐Whoa! There he is.
‐[snarls]
[Satoru breathing weakly]
Look, the kid's still breathing.
[Yukio] But he's in bad shape.
We have to hurry.
Don't move!
Another step, and I'll shoot.
[Rin] He's gone!
[Satoru breathing weakly]
Take it easy, kid,
we'll get you out of here.
[Yukio] It's a fake!
‐[Yukio] Ugggh!
‐Yukio!
[Yukio] Mr. Todo?
[Todo, younger voice] Oops.
I guess the jig's up.
Still, I can keep you busy
a bit longer.
‐[cocks gun]
‐[Yukio] Oh, my God!
He's gone over!
Rin, that boy
doesn't have much time.
Get him out of here! Hurry!
I'm on it!
Now, now, I can't have you
running off just yet.
‐[whoosh!]
‐[Rin groans]
[both scream]
[Yukio] Rin!
[Todo] You better stay focused,
or else...
[Yukio groaning]
[Todo] Believe it or not,
when I was your age,
I was a lot like you.
My family decided what course
my life would take
since the day I was born.
They didn't care
I had my own dreams
and I never complained.
And like a dog, I did
whatever they said and worked
for the good of the Order.
All I wanted was to be like
my dad and big brother.
So now, after a life like that,
do you know what I have
to show for it?
Nothing.
I decided the best thing
for me to do
was admit how I really felt.
My father, my brother,
the Order,
I hated them all,
and everything else
in this world.
That was all it took.
And once I admitted that,
I felt wonderful.
The missing piece in me had been
found and put into place.
[Yukio] You gave into
the temptations of a demon!
You're weak!
There's weakness
in the hearts of all humans.
Are you afraid
to acknowledge yours, boy?
[Yukio gasping]
‐[phone beeps]
‐Looks like my time's up here.
But before I go,
I just want to say
how happy I am
to have had this chat with you.
If what I said doesn't
make sense now, give it time.
You'll understand eventually.
When you do, I'll be there
to welcome you,
Yukio Okumura.
[Yukio] Wait!
[Rin] Yukio!
What do we do?
He's getting worse!
[Yukio] Your flames burned
the spores,
so they multiplied,
to try to repair themselves.
There's no time to get help.
I'll treat him here.
[Yukio panting]
[gasping] Damn this suit.
Dude, what are you...?
You're gonna get infected!
‐I can do it!
‐[Yukio] No, you've done enough!
I have to inject
the vaccine into the spore
without popping it.
Easy.
Damn it.
What's with my hands?
They're shaking like...
like when I was a kid.
I was so scared of demons,
I'd stand there shaking...
[boy whimpering]
just like now!
[Todo] All I wanted was to be
like my dad and big brother,
and after a life like that,
do you know what I have
to show for it?
Nothing.
There's weakness in the hearts
of all humans.
Are you afraid
to acknowledge yours, boy?
What are you doing?!
[Yukio groans]
[Yukio thinking] Like hell.
I'm not like you!
‐You're safe!
‐Mommy?
[mother] Thank you so much.
Not at all.
Nice work!
I expect nothing less
from our Mr. Okumura.
[Rin] Mephisto!
[Mephisto] Hmm.
What a god‐awful mess!
‐Quite the clever
diversion, though.
‐[Rin] Huh?
‐[Mephisto] The real
Left Eye was stolen.
‐[brothers gasp]
‐Don't freak out,
I got my familiar tracking it.
‐[Yukio] What, already?
I had a feeling
that Todo guy was shady,
so I snooped around,
and sure enough he is.
As if this wasn't enough,
the mischief makers
were attempting
a two‐pronged assault.
They also tried to liberate
the Right Eye
from our good friends
at our Kyoto facility.
‐[gulp]
‐What a bothersome situation.
What's up with
this Right‐Left Eye crap,
already?
[Mephisto] Anywhoo...
I'm assembling a crack team
to track the Left Eye down
and return it safely
to the academy.
Mr. Okumura, I'd like you
on that team.
‐But why me?
‐[Mephisto] Simple.
We don't know
what the enemy's goal is yet
and since you had contact
with him,
your presence
would be most beneficial.
I understand.
Lovely. See you
at the base in an hour.
Shura, watch him better.
Roger that.
Sheesh, he's the grumpiest
15‐year‐old ever.
He's gonna go bald soon.
[Rin] Hey, Yukio!
You think you're so rad!
One day I'll leave you behind!
Count on it!
You'll leave me behind?
Huh. You should work
on your jokes.
‐They're as lame as you are.
‐What?!
I can't baby‐sit you 24/7.
As you can see, I've got
more important things to do.
[Yukio thinking]
That's right, this is who I am.
[snarling] You stupid jerk!
I'll show you up someday,
and when I do,
it's gonna make your head spin!
[Rin] In middle school,
I didn't get to go
on the field trip to Kyoto,
so this'll be my first time.
I can't wait
to break that banana
out of my snack pack!
Your little "Yay, I get to go
on a trip" act's almost cute,
but this is work,
so get your ass on the train.
[passengers murmuring]
So, is it OK
if I just sit wherever?
Know what "read the room" means?
It means you sit up front.
While I'm checking out
how the vaccinations
are coming along
‐up in car three,
‐[Kuro mews]
you keep your ass in that seat
and stay out of trouble.
Yeah, I got it.
‐[Shura chuckles]
‐[Rin] Oh, yeah!
Oh, no way!
They got a tower in Kyoto, too?
Sweeeet!
Gotta make sure
to check that sucker out.
Rin.
Shiemi!
[Shiemi thinking]
What's wrong with me?
Wh‐Why can't I say anything?
Uh, Suguro, Miwa, Shima!
Good morning.
‐Morning.
‐Good morning, Moriyama.
[Konekomaru] Good morning.
Um, Ms. Kirigakure
wants you to go to car three
to get your vaccination.
Oh, right.
Hey, what up?
Glad to see you guys are OK.
Did you know Kyoto
had a friggin' tower?!
What am I saying?
Of course you did.
You're all from Kyoto.
Hey, you know any other cool
spots I can check out?
Let it go, Bon.
I know, I know.
Konekomaru.
Oh, come on, Konekomaru.
Don't blank him like that.
What are they thinking,
sending him with us?
What are we gonna do
if he goes on another rampage?
Hey, if that's what
the bigwigs want,
that's what they want.
Quit your stressing,
or you'll pop a blood vessel.
[Konekomaru] Shima, jeez,
how can you be so calm
about this?
[Rin thinking]
They're treating me
like I'm a rabid dog.
Hell, I can't say I blame 'em.
If I were them,
I'd feel the same way.
Yo, Izumo, I saved
this seat here for you.
‐[phone rings]
‐[Rin] Hmmmmm...?
[ringing continues]
‐What do you want?
‐[high‐pitched] Oh... nothing.
[train horn blares]
OK, listen up.
I'm Shura Kirigakure
and I got forced
into leading this op.
Hold the questions till after
I give you the rundown.
All right, so this morning,
someone snuck into the Deep Keep
and stole this hazardous
demonic thing called
the Left Eye
of the Impure King.
We know the thief
wasn't working alone.
He got help from the warden,
Senior Second Class Exorcist
Saburota Todo.
As for why it was stolen
and how many others were
involved, we don't know yet.
Over in Kyoto,
same time this was going on,
someone was trying
to break into their Deep Keep.
They were after the Right Eye
of the Impure King.
They failed this time,
but we think they'll try again.
Excuse me, ma'am, I don't know
who this Impure King is.
We haven't studied him.
[Shura] That's probably
'cause he's not one
of the better‐known demons.
The Impure King
is an upper‐level creep
that spread plagues
in the late Edo period.
Thanks to him, 40,000 people
died from fever and disease.
A priest called Fukaku
took him down.
To prove he was the one
that did it,
he gouged out the King's
left and right eyes.
Thing is, the eyes give off
a toxic miasma,
so they're super dangerous.
He gouged them out?
What the hell was he thinking?
That Fukaku guy sounds
like a show‐off.
Oh, my God.
So, anycrap,
even though we don't know
what the enemy wants to do
with the eyes yet,
we're pretty damn sure it's
gonna be for something nasty.
As long as the Right Eye's
at the Kyoto branch,
it's a cinch
it'll get attacked again.
The mission is,
care for the wounded Exorcists
and beef up security
in case those scumbags make
another play for the eye.
And I expect
all you ExWires to help out.
And lastly, teamwork,
do your best, blah‐blah‐blah.
And please don't make
extra work for me.
Why aren't you scared of me
like everyone else?
Me, scared of you?
That's the stupidest thing ever.
What, 'cause you're
half‐human, half‐demon?
Let me tell you something,
there's lots of people
who are a mix of the two.
In fact, I know there's
a ton of Exorcists who are.
No way. Seriously?
In my opinion,
the only problem
anyone has with you
is that you're
the son of Satan.
I bet the Order is still
trying to figure out
if having you on their side
is a pro or a con.
That's probably why
they haven't killed you yet.
You're making a big fuss
over nothing,
like a certain bonehead
in our class
who I'm not going to name.
Polkabrows.
Polka what?!
You're trying to cheer me up,
ain't ya, Polkabrows?
‐Huh?
‐I knew it.
You're a nice person, after all.
What are you saying?
I am not!
And for your information,
my name is Izumo Kamiki!
Don't give me stupid nicknames!
Still, Izumo, thank you.
We are not
on a first‐name basis!
[Shura] Christ,
put a sock in it!
There are people trying to get
some shuteye in here.
You bunch of cowards!
"I wanna defeat Satan!
I wanna protect my friends!"
It's a lot of big talk is all.
Heck, whenever things
get tough,
everyone forgets
their grand statements!
OK, lady, I've had it
with your big mouth.
Who are you calling a coward?
Hmm. What else
should I call you?
Stop it! We're supposed to be
on the same team.
Team?
That's right.
Why can't you trust me, man?
Me, trust you?
How can I?
[dramatic soundtrack plays]
[crying]
Konekomaru!
Stop!
[snarls]
Guys! You're OK?
Bastard.
How could you let
the son of Satan in here?!
Hey, it's no big deal, Suguro.
I don't look all that different
from a normal human, do I?
Heh. Except for the dumb tail,
I mean.
‐[chuckles]
‐[Shiemi whimpers]
How could you?
‐It's not funny!
‐[Rin] But I didn't‐‐
There's nothing funny
about this!
Shiemi.
[Yukio] Fifteen years ago,
my brother Rin was born.
His mother was human,
Satan was his father.
He inherited the power
of Satan's blue flames.
[all gasp]
Um... I don't mean to pry,
but you and he are twins,
so does that mean
you have that power, too?
[Yukio] No. I didn't inherit it.
I check myself for it
every day.
As far as I know,
I'm still human.
The man who raised us
sealed Rin's flames away
in the Koma Sword.
That's why,
for the past 15 years,
he's lived a normal life,
like any other human kid.
But his power became too great
for the sword to contain
and about three months ago,
it awoke.
[Shiemi thinking]
Three months ago?
Up until that day, he grew up
not knowing who he really was.
But why? What did your dad hope
to get out of raising him?
[Yukio] I'm sorry.
I wish I knew the answer.
[sighs]
[Shiemi whimpering]
Sixteen years ago,
on the Blue Night,
my temple's followers
were killed by blue flames
like yours.
That's right,
your blue flames kill people!
People like my grandpa,
and Shima's grandpa
and oldest brother.
And Konekomaru's family!
[Rin thinking] What?
The followers at my temple
are like family to me.
So how do you expect me
to trust you
after what you did
to my family?!
Look, man, I'm sorry
you went through that.
That's got nothing to do
with me.
Don't blame me
for what happened!
[Konekomaru] Bon!
You talk a good game.
Like how you said you wanna
beat the shit out of Satan!
That's right.
So don't you lump me in
with him!
[Suguro snarls]
[Shura] Girls.
You do this when shit gets
real, you know what happens?
You die!
[Suguro groans]
Exorcists can't fight
the good fight on their own.
Like it or not, you better learn
to work together.
[snake]
Straight down
thissss road.
[snake
rattling]
Yukio.
Wanna join me,
fight together?
[Yukio] Huh?
You wanna be afraid forever,
or do you wanna be strong
so you can protect Rin
and other people?
[Yukio] Huh?
Protect Rin?
I can do that?
Really?
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyo" in Japanese]
We got the enemy
right outside our door,
so now's not the time
to be fighting!
Hmm. If you feel that strongly
about it, Ryuji,
go tell that to your father,
the so‐called master.
[Suguro] Watch your damn mouth,
Mamushi!
[Tatsuma] So, uh,
what's your name?
‐[Rin] It's Rin Okumura.
‐[Tatsuma] Really?
I've heard of you.