[Kuro mewing]
‐Juzo.
‐Dad! Those flames.
Don't worry about that now.
Our priority is to find
the Right Eye.
Listen, I want you
to tail the Master.
Stay close,
but stay out of sight.
[Juzo] The Master?
[Yaozo coughs]
[Tatsuma] Rin's lucky to have
a guardian like you,
Ms. Kirigakure.
I'll say.
Yeah. That's one fine tushy.
[snarls]
‐Hands off!
‐[priests] Ohh!
Keep an eye on Rin
for me, will ya?
[Kuro mews]
[Shura] Pretty quick
for an old fart.
[phone rings]
Shura here.
Oh, hey, Yukio.
How's the hunt
for the Left Eye?
Are things going OK
over there?
Huh? Over here?
Um... We had a thing happen.
Huh?!
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyou" in Japanese]
[Shura] Yukio.
Hi, Shura.
Hey, what's going on?
‐I'm sorry I couldn't
get through to you sooner.
‐Yeah, why didn't you?
Our calls were being jammed,
so we decided to stop by.
Anyway, you said
something happened.
What's up?
Yeah. Well, you see, um...
I'm Yaozo Shima,
director of this field office.
You must be the teen that was
sent to retrieve the Left Eye.
I welcome you to Kyoto.
Since we have
all the senior staff present,
we should talk about
the recent developments.
This way, please.
[whooshing]
[panting]
[coughing]
[whoosh]
‐Are you going to be OK?
‐[panting]
I hope the strain
of this responsibility
isn't too much for you.
No. I'm fine.
I can keep going.
I couldn't forgive myself
if anything happened to you.
But I'm just not strong enough
to handle both the eyes
on my own.
‐Maybe we should take a break.
‐I'm fine!
[panting]
I'm fine.
We can rest after
we get these vile things
somewhere safe.
[panting]
[Yaozo] The Right Eye was stolen
from our field office,
and I'm embarrassed to say
the thief is one of our own.
She was behind
the earlier attempt.
At least that's the assumption
we're going on.
[Uwabami] Her name
is Mamushi Hojo,
intermediate exorcist
first class
and leader
of the Keep security.
We thought we had her trapped,
but she managed to escape
with Todo's assistance.
I'm sorry. I wish we could
have got here faster.
If they're together, then Todo
has both the left and right eyes
in his possession now.
Dammit. I was afraid of that.
The car we were tracking
was just a decoy.
We searched it and found
two dead exorcists inside.
And then,
when we tried reporting it,
we found out someone
was jamming our cell phones.
It was all a ploy to buy time.
This is terrible!
If he has both eyes, then...
‐[coughing]
‐Take it easy.
What's gonna happen
if he has both eyes?
Could you explain?
The Myoda,
for better or for worse,
has kept secrets within secrets
for the past 150 years.
And what exactly does that mean?
It means there are many things
us elders don't even know about.
But our high priest,
Tatsuma Suguro,
knows all our secrets.
There is, however, one secret
‐that is made known only
to the elders.
‐Which is?
[Yaozo] According to the legend
of the Impure King,
a story passed down among
the upper ranks of priests,
when his left and right eyes
are brought together,
a new and more potent miasma
will be unleashed upon
the world.
Todo wants to gas everyone?
No way. There has to be
more to it.
The miasma from one eye
was bad enough.
It'll be even worse
from both.
And if it comes to that,
it might be more
than the Knights
of the True Cross can handle.
I would say our priority's
pretty clear here:
find Todo and Mamushi stat.
[Yaozo] We have our people
searching all the places
we think they'd be
likely to hide.
But since they vanished
into thin air,
they didn't leave us
a trail to follow.
We need doctors
and meisters here, right now.
With them on the loose,
we should prepare ourselves
for the worst outcome.
[Yukio] Why would he wait
to release the miasma?
Why didn't he do it
when he got the Right Eye?
Maybe ground zero
is somewhere else.
Or maybe he's got other plans.
‐[Yukio groaning]
‐[Todo] Believe it or not,
when I was your age,
I was a lot like you.
My family decided what course
my life would take
since the day I was born.
They didn't care I had
my own dreams
and I never complained.
And like a dog, I did
whatever they said and worked
for the good of the Order.
So now, after a life like that,
do you know what I have
to show for it?
Nothing. If what I said
doesn't make sense now,
give it time.
You'll understand eventually.
When you do,
I'll welcome you with open arms,
Yukio Okumura.
[Yukio] Todo.
You're after something else.
Something much more sinister.
[Shura] Yukio.
‐Um, yes.
‐We gotta talk.
It's about that thing
I mentioned on the phone
earlier.
Huh?
So what is it?
Hmm. Yeah.
‐So, um...
‐It's about Rin, isn't it?
Oh! Damn, you're just
as sharp as ever.
What did he do this time?
Well, he sort of flared up
in front of everyone.
[Yukio groans]
He's such an idiot!
All right.
Where is my brother now?
[Shiro] The Koma Sword.
Also known as Kurikara.
An ancient and legendary
demon‐slaying sword.
Many years ago,
I transferred your demonic
powers to this sword
and sealed the scabbard.
Once drawn, your demonic powers
will be awakened
and you can never go back
to being human.
[growls]
[groaning]
[shouting battle cries]
[snarling]
[inaudible dialogue]
[bystanders murmuring]
[Rin] Shut up!
All this dumb talk about me's
starting to piss me off!
You sit there
sticking labels on people!
I ain't a weapon or a demon king
or a savior!
I'm Rin Okumura!
One day, I'll be the most
powerful exorcist ever,
and don't you bastards
forget it!
[Yukio]
It was crazy to think he could
pass the exam in six months.
Now his life is hanging
by a thread.
They'll execute him
for sure after this.
Yeah, it totally sucks.
What do we do now?
Never had to deal
with crap like this before.
Don't be so glib.
I swore on my father's grave
I'd protect Rin, no matter what.
[Shura] On that note,
you know what it takes
to be a good exorcist?
[Yukio] Skill, stamina
and heart.
[Shura] Yeah, but
the most important thing
is to not control
your emotions so much.
Demons take advantage of that.
Thank you.
Pent‐up anger and stress
give them a way in.
Rin's got the makings
of a good exorcist
'cause he doesn't
hold anything back.
A person like you,
on the other hand,
is the real danger.
You're the type
that gets turned.
Try cutting loose,
open up for a change
and see what happens.
[Yukio] All right,
you asked for it.
I've hated you
since the day I met you.
Whoa! [chuckles]
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about.
[chuckles]
Uh‐uh. You are not
still working.
Oh, yeah, I guess.
See? I'm making fever reducers,
but I'm almost done.
Yeah, that's great and all,
but didn't you feel
that earthquake?
Earthquake? Oh!
That's what that shaking was.
Oh, brother. Talk about getting
lost in your work.
[giggles]
Whatevs. At least you're in
a good mood again.
Tough as a weed, no joke.
[giggles] A person can't stay
all mopey forever.
Well, the important thing is
that you're back to what
you're normally like.
What am I normally like?
Can you tell me?
Huh? Are you serious?
You're always cheerful,
in a ditzy way.
Plus, you're brave, 'cause
you're not afraid to walk up
and talk to anyone.
That's you in a nutshell.
Is... is that how
everyone sees me?
No way.
What?
Nothing.
It's just that...
I'm not like that.
Truth is, I thought,
after all this time together,
we're all becoming
better friends.
But I didn't really know
Rin and Yuki
and about all the stuff
they were dealing with.
You feel bad 'cause you didn't
know Rin was Satan's son?
I spent so much time around him,
and I had no idea.
When they were taking him away,
I realized I couldn't do
anything for him.
Then I freaked out.
I lost confidence in everything
I did after that.
I managed to screw up
even the simplest things.
I don't even have the guts
to talk to Rin anymore.
You know what?
That just means
I have to work harder.
And I'll start
by doing the laundry.
Do you want Rin to be
more than... you know?
‐Excuse me!
‐[gasps]
‐Dang, Izumo, you look
so hot in that!
‐[scoffs]
[Konekomaru]
Miss Moriyama, quick.
We need some ice.
Bon's been hurt!
Oh, sure. What?
Are you gonna tell us
what happened?
The Right Eye was stolen
from the field office.
[all gasp]
No way. For real?
For real.
Then they took Okumura away.
‐No!
‐Why? What did he do?
His flames came out
and damn near everyone saw 'em.
[flames whooshing]
Well... then where is he now?
At the field office,
locked in a cell.
So, like, now he's, like,
in trouble?
Like serious trouble?
Rin.
[footsteps]
[Shura] So, you cool off yet?
How ya feelin', kiddo?
Still a little wobbly.
But I can move OK, I guess.
‐You're up.
‐Huh?
Uh...
Is this how
you're gonna show me up,
by getting thrown in jail?
And all that big talk
about making my head spin.
I don't even know what to say.
While you were conked out,
Suguro's dad slipped this to me.
Guess he wanted me
to give it to you.
What's it say?
It's addressed to you, dude.
Open it.
Interesting.
Well, what's it say?
‐I can't read it.
‐Huh?!
Jeez! I knew you were
a dumbass,
but this is
un‐freakin‐believable!
Kids these days make me worry
about the future.
No way!
I can't read it either!
‐That's what I was saying!
‐It's cursive script.
I can read enough to get by.
OK, Mr. Okumura.
Translate it for the class.
Go on, chop‐chop.
I want to hear what the old fart
has to say, so get on with it.
He might tell us something about
this mess with the eyes.
OK, here goes.
"Greetings, Rin Okumura.
Allow me to introduce myself.
[Tatsuma] I am a priest
who lives in Kyoto
and my name is Tatsuma Suguro.
[straining]
I'm sure you're wondering
why I'm writing you,
and the reason is, I have
an important favor to ask.
You're probably confused
as to why a total stranger
would be asking you for favors,
so I'll begin by telling you
a little about my past.
I'm not too good of a writer,
so forgive me if things
get a little jumbled.
I guess the best place
for me to start
would be before
you and Ryuji were born.
Hold on, it's not working?
She's not better?
[pained breathing]
Torako.
[Tatsuma]
I was much younger then,
and my pregnant wife
had become very ill.
I was so worried.
She grew weaker by the day,
and I was powerless
to help her.
The miasma from the Right Eye
of the Impure King
is what made her so sick.
Ah, Torako!
Hi, Tatsuma.
Torako?
Don't worry, it's OK.
The baby and I are fine.
Go back to work, honey.
OK.
[Yukio] Tatsuma.
The Master wishes to see you.
Tatsuma, what do you think
you're doing?
You cannot neglect
your duties.
Protecting everyone from
the Right Eye's poison
is your responsibility.
You must pray to the Buddha
every day without fail.
If you don't, he will
forsake you and take
his power away from you.
But... I have prayed.
I've prayed
for the last seven years.
In all that time, 15 people have
died instead of getting better.
Torako can't take it.
If this keeps up,
she and our baby are going to...
Can I really save everyone
by tending the sacred flame?!
Is there anything else you can
do for her besides tend it?
Uh...
The best way
to fight this evil
is by honoring the teachings
of our noble ancestor without...
‐[coughing]
‐Father!
We're done talking.
I must go back to my duties.
[coughing continues]
Even after my mother died
and he'd gotten sick himself,
my father kept up his duties
to Myoda day in, day out,
without fail.
One day, son, my duties
will be yours.
When I die,
the true secrets of this temple
will be passed down to you.
And for the rest of your life,
you must dedicate yourself
to keeping them safe.
Secrets?
If Torako doesn't survive,
find a new wife
of hardier stock.
Having a successor is yet
another of your duties.
Clear your mind
and relinquish desire.
I was powerless,
so I accepted his words.
At birth, I became the 17th
in the line of high priests
of Myoda.
Each and every day,
the monks of our sect
carried out their duties
in order to protect
that bloodline.
And I had duties of my own
to fulfill.
As long as my mind
was clear of doubt,
I could protect Myoda
and Torako
and her unborn child.
I forced myself
to believe that.
Then one day...
[creature shrieks]
...out of the sky...
[shrieking]
[priests scream]
‐[gun fires repeatedly]
‐[creature groans]
‐What the...
‐Protect the young Master!
[creature wails]
I don't believe it.
The sacred flame.
[Shiro] Holy shit, that hurt!
Ugggh!
‐[priests] Tatsuma!
‐[priests snarling]
[dramatic music plays]
[Shiro] What's up
with this mountain?
It's crawling with monsters.
Typical of Mephisto
and his janky intel.
My gun's too small,
I'm out of ammo.
Should have brought a cannon.
‐Hey, who are you?!
‐[Shiro] Me.
We were performing
a sacred ritual
and you ruined it!
Get down here!
[Shiro] Ooh, lookie
what we have here.
[gasps] Oh, no.
[Shiro] Ain't this
a Koma Sword?
News flash: it's mine now.
Huh? What?
[snorts]
[Tatsuma] That was when I met
Shiro Fujimoto,
the man who raised you,
the man you call your father.
Are you insane?
You can't have it.
That's Myoda's sacred relic!
[gasping]
Oh, my God.
I had no idea
our fathers knew each other.
That's how Dad got his hands
on the Koma Sword?
No way.
It belongs to Suguro's temple?
[groans] Don't stop now,
keep reading!
Uh, right.
[Tatsuma panting]
I'm beat. Fifteen years ago,
I could do this, no sweat.
Oh, well.
At least now I get to put
my purpose in life to the test.
[panting]
Watch over me, Shiro,
you scoundrel!
[Rin Akatsuki singing
"Kono Te De" in Japanese]
[Shiro] I'm gonna kill
a kid with this.
[Tatsuma] Give it back!
That's sacred to us!
[Shiro] Oh, shut up.
This is all bullshit!
[Tatsuma] Can you save them?
[Shiro] I hate guys like you
worse than anything!
[Mamushi] If I go through
with this, the others
will never forgive me.
[Todo] Are you having
any regrets?
[Mamushi] Mr.Todo,
what are you, really?