[thud]
[Suguro] I can't take
this shit anymore.
I've asked you all to this
meeting today for one reason...
to find out which one of us
is the traitor!
On that day, it looked to me
as if the Master were
controlling the flames.
Surely, he's not behind this.
That's insane.
The fact is, if he wasn't
involved, he'd be here
trying to figure out who was.
I'm going to Kongo‐Shinzan
in the morning
and make Dad tell me
what's going on.
Huh?
[footsteps]
Juzo!
[priest] Excuse me, sir?
Yes?
[priest] We heard about
the meeting earlier
this afternoon with the elders.
Is something going on
we should know about?
No. Why?
Did someone tell you there was?
The thing is, we thought
maybe something came up
at the meeting you were at,
because all the senior exorcists
in charge of the Keep security
were told the director wanted
to see them ASAP.
‐And this is happening now?
‐Yes, sir.
‐[Juzo] Where?
‐[priest] I don't know.
But after what happened
the other day down there,
it's kind of odd to leave
the Keep's defenses so thin,
don't you think?
[Juzo] Yeah. I'll go find
the director and talk to him.
Thank you.
[keys jingle]
[lock turns]
[Suguro] The key
to the field office.
What's he suddenly
going there for?
[bell dings]
[gasps]
Hey, what happened here?!
[priest groaning]
[Suguro] What the hell
are you up to, Juzo?
[priests groaning]
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyou" in Japanese]
[Rin] Stay calm. Relax.
Don't think too hard
about lighting them.
Just stay calm
and let it happen.
‐[drums beating]
‐[Rin] Hmm?!
‐[buzzer sounds]
‐[Rin groans]
[roars]
[buzzer sounds]
[groans]
It's not about setting
the candle on fire...
All I wanna burn is that part.
I just need a tiny bit
of flame to light it.
Just one little flick
of fire and...
‐[gasps]
‐Whoa!
[Kuro] Oooh!
I did it.
Yeah, I did it!
‐[Rin laughing]
‐[Kuro] Yay!
‐[Rin] I did it!
‐[Kuro mewing]
See that, Shura?
I lit those suckers
like a bad‐ass! Whoo!
[Shura, yawning]
Yeah, you sure did.
Congratulations.
You can finally get started
on your training now.
Wait, I thought I was training.
Why have I been killing
all these candles?!
You have to control your flames
all the time,
not once in a while.
How many times have
I gotta say it?
If you let them get
out of control again,
it's over for you
[Timowan] Let us get straight
to the point.
Is the creature before us
the son of Satan?
[Mephisto] That he is,
your honor.
I simply can't hide the truth
from you any longer.
And what was your reason
for having Shiro Fujimoto
raise the boy in secret?
[chuckles]
Why, to fight Satan, milady.
To make him a weapon
for the Order.
May I have everyone's attention?
I would like to propose
the following wager to you.
Will the spawn of Satan become
the demon king of Gehenna
or the savior of the Order?
No, of Assiah.
Place your bets, please!
‐[man] Preposterous!
‐[woman] This is an outrage!
[crowd jeering]
Sir Pheles, we, the Grigori,
accept the wager
put forth by you.
However, certain conditions
must be met.
First, he must pass
the Exorcist Authorization Exam
in six months.
Second, if he is determined
at any time to be
a threat to Assiah,
he shall be declared
an exorcism target
and executed immediately.
[Rin snarls]
Yeah, you're right, I still got
a long ways to go.
[chuckles] But still,
I lit 'em!
It might be a small step
for one man,
but it's a huge‐ass leap
for mankind!
What the hell
are you talking about?
‐Get back to practicing, doofus.
‐[Rin chuckles]
[priest groaning]
[Juzo] What do you think
you're doing over there,
Mamushi?
[Suguro thinking] Mamushi?
[keys jingle]
I knew it.
You're the one who betrayed us.
The trick with the sacred flame
was a nice touch.
I didn't suspect you until you
started pointing fingers
at me at the meeting.
I'll be honest,
maybe we never clicked,
but I did admire you.
No one else was as dedicated
to Myoda as you were.
So why did you do it?
Say something!
[Mamushi] I did it
to open Myoda's eyes.
There are two traitors.
One is Tatsuma Suguro!
The other is
the Order's precept,
Mephisto Pheles.
Mephisto?
Mephisto? Why do you think that?
Eight years ago,
when we began our studies
at the cram school
for exorcists,
Mr. Todo asked me
to his office one day.
‐Miss Hojo.
‐Yes, sir.
[Todo] What I'm about
to tell you is confidential.
Have you heard of the Left Eye
of the Impure King?
What?
[Todo] The precept,
Mephisto Pheles,
is storing the Left Eye
in the Deep Keep.
He says it's
his personal property.
Supposedly, a Right Eye
is also said to exist.
To be honest,
this is all quite mysterious.
Since you're from the Myoda sect
and they defeated
the Impure King,
I was wondering if you knew
anything about it.
The Left Eye?
But this is the first time
I've ever heard about it.
Oh, that is unusual.
It is.
[Todo, voice fading]
Now I'm really concerned.
I don't think the precept...
[Mamushi] So we talked.
He told me he had been
suspicious of Mephisto
for a long time.
He wanted to expose
the precept's corruption.
[Juzo] What?
[Mamushi] Something else
Mr. Todo found out
was that Tatsuma Suguro was
also involved in the treachery.
For the past few years, I've
been cooperating with Mr. Todo,
and I've been doing
my own investigating.
I dug and dug and dug,
but I couldn't find
anything, really.
Till a week ago.
I found out a disciplinary
hearing had been held
at the Vatican.
Mephisto was the one
being questioned.
It turns out, Mephisto had
spared the son of Satan's life
and was raising him in secret.
He did what?!
[Mamushi] It's true,
and what's worse is,
he used the most sacred relic
of Myoda to seal his powers.
You understand
what that means, don't you?
It means Mephisto was
involved in a conspiracy,
just as Mr. Todo suspected.
And Tatsuma Suguro helped him.
Can you prove it?
What, do you think I have
the evidence with me?
No matter.
It will all be clear soon.
[Mamushichanting spell]
We can't trust our superiors
anymore.
[wind whooshing]
[hisses]
[Mamushi] Mr. Todo will help us.
He'll take the right
and left eyes and seal them away
somewhere safe.
Stop it, Mamushi!
Think about what you're doing.
If what you say is true,
you should tell the elders!
[Mamushi, scoffing]
The elders.
Even though Tatsuma sold
Myoda out to the Knights
of the True Cross,
our elders would never
accuse him of anything.
Even my own father wouldn't!
Do you think they'd believe
what I just told you?!
And your father? Hah!
He's even worse!
I could hand him the evidence
on a platter,
and he'd just laugh
and say I was imagining things.
There's no time
for playing those games.
Well, things have escalated
sooner than we thought.
Master?
Yes, I've heard enough.
[coughs]
I'll have the senior exorcist
on standby to take her
into custody.
Is that OK, Uwabami?
Mamushi's an adult now.
Yes. Do it.
‐[hisses]
‐[Juzo] This is wrong, Mamushi.
[Mamushi] I don't need
your approval.
I'm doing this to save Myoda!
[Juzo groans]
[Juzo] Fine then.
We were friends once,
and now it's up to me
to stop you!
Mamushi, Juzo, stop it!
Calm down and let's
talk this over!
‐[building rumbling]
‐Aaah!
[Rin] What the hell?
Everything's shaking.
[sniffs]
[Kuro] Over there!
Something's up
at the field office.
Rin, stay here
and keep on...
‐[bell clangs]
‐Huh?
Huuuuh?!
[Shura snarls]
[Rin screams]
Yo, where do you think
you're going?!
I'm your guardian
and I told you to stay!
‐I got it, I got it!
‐[Shura snarls]
‐You damn well better!
‐[Rin] Ow ow ow ow ow!
[Rin] Oww!
What do we do?
‐[earth rumbles]
‐[Rin] Ohh!
Ah, what the hell.
Come on, kid.
‐[alarm wailing]
‐What's going on?
That's no earthquake.
[Tatsuma] It's an intruder!
Get to the Keep!
‐[alarm ringing]
‐Hey, you know what's going on?
The Keep's being
broken into again!
‐[rumbling]
‐[Suguro straining]
[Suguro] What the hell's
going on?
[rumbling continues]
[Juzo] The ceiling.
It's rotting!
Mamushi!
Why, hello, Mr. Shima.
So good to see you again.
Todo! You devil!
You tricked Mamushi into this!
[Todo chuckles]
[Todo] Devil, am I?
[chuckles]
I like it, but you're wrong
about me tricking her.
Actually, Ms. Hojo asked
for my help.
What he says is true.
Stealing the eyes was my idea.
I don't believe that!
He's brainwashing you!
Come on, Mamushi!
Can't you see he's messing
with your head?
Snap out of it!
Don't do it.
You're out of your mind!
Stop!
I know what I'm doing.
‐You're the ones being tricked.
‐[air whooshing]
[priests straining]
[priest] What happened?!
[surprised murmuring]
No way. I can't believe it.
Mamushi was the traitor?
Where'd they go?
[murmuring continues]
[Yaozo] Quiet, everyone.
Now's not the time to panic.
We have to regroup.
[footsteps]
‐Long time, no see, Dad.
‐[Tatsuma chuckles]
Ryuji!
Yeah, it has been a while.
That sure is one heck
of a mohawk you got going on.
‐[Suguro] Going somewhere?
‐[Tatsuma laughs nervously]
Actually, yeah.
To go find Mamushi.
Can't have her out there
with that eye, can we?
‐You mind letting me go?
‐You're going after Mamushi,
huh?
Do you know why she betrayed us,
why we're in this mess now?
It's 'cause of you!
This is your fault!
You should have been
at the meeting
instead of farting around!
Suguro...
[Shura] You know the old guy?
[Rin] Yeah. That's Suguro's dad.
You better start talking, Dad.
Is it true what Mamushi said,
that you betrayed us?
I... What are you saying?
Of course not.
OK then, why don't you tell
everyone, right here, right now,
what you've been up to?
You really wanna know, huh?
Sorry, son, it's a secret.
I can't tell anyone what it is.
Ever.
Not even my own son.
How can you say that
after what just happened here?
Yeah, well, I have to go
after Mamushi.
Listen, be a good boy and do
what your mom and teachers
tell you.
Oh, and stay out of trouble.
Got it, son?
Drop the act, already!
[soft murmuring]
You're only ever around
when it's convenient for you.
This time, if you bail now
without explaining yourself,
then as far as I'm concerned,
you're not my dad anymore!
Gimme a break!
You're not my father.
You're nobody to me.
Don't ever let me see you
acting like my father again!
Ugggh!
That boy is my son,
and I'm taking him back.
Oh, Dad!
I, uh...
I really should get going.
Try and forgive me.
[Tatsuma groans]
[Rin] Wait.
Huh? Crap.
He gave me the slip again.
‐O... Okumura!
‐[Rin] Why are you walking away?
You're supposed to be his dad,
ain't ya?
‐Rin, I...
‐You cool leaving it like this?
Well, are ya?
And as for you, Suguro,
quit being an ass!
‐[crowd shouting]
‐[Juzo] Bon!
‐[Shura] Rin!
[Suguro groans]
‐[priest 1] Are you all right?
‐[priest 2] Bon!
[priestess] Did you see
a flash of light just now?
[Rin] I don't know what went
down between you guys before,
but I know you're both gonna
regret this later on!
Apologize!
Tell your dad you're sorry,
while you still can!
What do you know?
This ain't your business!
Stay out of it!
He's your dad, man.
You can't push him away
like this!
Yeah, right,
like you're one to talk.
Now, now, boys,
let's everybody cool down.
Why don't you shake hands
and make up?
What are you still doing here?
You know where the door is.
Leave.
And don't come back!
[Rin whimpers]
[flames whoosh]
I used to think you were
the coolest.
‐No, Rin!
‐[Rin] I used to look up to you!
But you're not cool at all.
You're an asshole!
‐What's happening to him?!
‐[priest] He's on fire!
I can't believe it.
Blue flames.
Excuse me,
coming through here.
That's enough, Rin!
‐You don't get it.
‐[Rin snarls]
[Suguro chanting spell]
[Rin groans]
[Shura] Down, Rin! Heel! Heel!
[sparks zapping]
You've got no idea.
It ain't like I wanna be
Satan's kid!
My situation ain't
the same as yours!
It ain't, is it?
Tell your dad you're sorry.
It'll be too late
when he's dead!
Don't make the same mistake
I did!
Tell him you're sorry! Now!
[Juzo] Bon!
Aaah!
‐Juzo!
‐Don't worry, Bon, I got this.
Hurry. Get out
while you still can.
[Mamushi] Mephisto had spared
the son of Satan's life
and was raising him in secret.
[Juzo thinking]
This is the kid.
And Renzo's his friend.
I can't believe it!
[Shura recites chant]
‐[Rin shrieks]
‐[Kuro mews]
Rin, calm down.
Did you forget what the Grigori
said the other day
at the hearing?
[Rin groaning]
You can't lose it.
Get a grip or you'll be
executed as a demon.
I don't care!
I'm having a conversation here.
So butt out of it!
Bitch!
OK.
‐[Shura chanting spell]
‐[Rin howling]
That boy, is he...?
[Shura finishes spell]
[Kuro] Rin?! Rin!
[Shura] Dumb ass.
Hey, um, can I get a hand
taking this doofus to a cell?
He's out cold
so he won't bite ya, promise.
I hope so,
Ms. Kirigakure.
Director! I'm so terribly sorry
for causing such a scene!
Yes, well, then I expect you'll
stop by to explain it later?
Of course I will, sir.
[Kuro] Rin! Rin!
[Rin Akatsuki singing
"Kono Te De" in Japanese]
I hope the strain
of this responsibility
isn't too much for you.
Keep an eye on Rin for me,
will ya?
[Shura]Todo wants
to gas everyone?
[Yukio]No way.
There has to be more to it.
[Shura] He sort of flared up
in front of everyone.
[Yukio] He's such an idiot!
[Tatsuma] Watch over me,
Shura, you scoundrel!