[roaring]
[Suguro] Okumura!
[snarling]
[Impure King growls]
Okumura!
[Rin thinking] I drew it!
[straining]
[Shura chanting spell]
Shura!
Don't worry,
I'll take care of him!
That monster's way too powerful
for an ordinary human to handle.
You're the only one who can.
Remember what you told me?
You swore on Shiro's grave
you'd be like him
and that he was right
to save your life.
So, are you ready to prove it?!
Hell yeah!
Go get him!
Rin, all you ever needed
was a little self‐confidence.
And now that you've got it,
show us what you're made of.
[Rin snarls]
[Impure King groaning]
This thing's tough!
How the hell am I
gonna kill it?!
It looks like this isn't
gonna be easy.
[panting]
Suguro!
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyou" in Japanese]
‐[priests gasping]
‐[Yaozo] The barrier!
Bon! Something must
have happened to Bon!
Whoa! Hold the phone.
All that gas
is gonna hit the city now!
No. With the rain
coming down this hard,
it should keep the miasma
from heading down the mountain.
For now, anyway.
I knew they couldn't
keep the barrier up.
Alas, what to do.
[exploding]
The lid has blown off of Hell.
‐[priests murmuring]
‐[distant jingling]
[Ucchusma] You humans
are so worthless.
[Rin straining] Damn it!
What am I gonna do?
I can't let this stuff
get loose!
To the Exorcists fighting
the monster below,
allow me to offer a quote
from Nietzsche's
Beyond Good and Evil.
"He who fights with monsters
might take care
lest he thereby become
a monster."
Ooh, but this next part
is my absolute favorite:
"When you gaze long
into an abyss,
the abyss also gazes
into you."
‐[whoosh]
‐[Yukio gasps]
[Yukio] Todo!
Where is he?
I can't believe
he can regenerate so fast.
Gotta stay alert!
[Todo laughing]
[Todo] See? I warned you
not to underestimate
Karura's ability to heal me.
You and your friends don't have
what it takes to kill me yet.
Nice try, though.
Now that I have a handle
on Karura's powers,
there's not much point
hanging around anymore.
But before I go,
you should know this,
Yukio Okumura.
You have my attention now.
You monster!
[Todo] Huh! I'm a monster?
Aren't you one too?
Isn't that why you
hate yourself?
Such naive self‐loathing.
The first step
to becoming just like me.
I'm nothing like you,
you demon!
[Yukio thinking] Demon.
That's right.
He's a demon.
Can't believe I almost forgot
the basic rule of exorcism:
don't let a demon's words
get to you.
Thanks to the rain,
these magic naiad bullets
should be two or three times
more powerful than normal.
I have to stay calm.
[groaning]
[Todo] What is your problem
with demons, anyway?
Your brother's one, so why
do you hate them so much?
They're not so bad.
And besides, you have a little
bit of demon in you, too.
Come on now, let's see it again.
[straining]
[Yukio thinking]
I'm not a demon!
[Todo] Hmm?
[Yukio] I'm not like you!
[sighs]
Why do you keep resisting
your true nat...
[coughs]
Mr. Shima, how could you?
[gunshot]
[Yukio] Time's run out for you,
demon!
Who are you, really?
What are you after here?
Splendid. The expression
on your face suits you.
That's the face of a demon,
the real you, without a doubt.
As for who I am, I won't tell.
At least, not until you accept
who you are.
Then die!
[gasping]
[coughing]
Are you OK?
[Yukio] I'm fine.
But it looks like some
of your team could use a hand.
He'll regenerate before long.
We should forget
about him for now.
We need to get out of here.
[Juzo] Let's meet up with
our main force inside the bar...
What the hell's going on?
The rain's suppressing
the miasma, so let's take
advantage of it while we can.
We'll regroup
with the main force!
Damn it!
That's the face of a demon,
the real you, without a doubt.
[Yukio thinking] Damn! Damn!
Damn it!
Yes! Gaze into the abyss!
[roars]
[Rin thinking] What was
the point in letting me live?!
Dad!
Give me the strength
to kill this thing!
[Ucchusma] I cannot bear
to watch this any longer!
[gasps]
Who are you?!
Uh... a demon?
[Ucchusma] Ehh.
Demon. Angel. Myo‐O.
What does it matter?
Those are human terms
which have no meaning to me.
You, on the other hand,
what does one call a human
wrapped in divine flames?
I am Ucchusma, the guardian
who purifies the unclean.
And the Impure King is an enemy
of mine from long ago.
The sword you hold in your hand
was once my lord's
personal weapon.
If you truly wish
to defeat the Impure King,
I can instruct you on how to
harness the power of the flame
and channel it.
Damn, man.
That's a lot of big words.
OK, show me how!
Then let us begin!
Ooh!
I shall now chant
the mantra and sutra.
You must repeat them after me.
Wait. What are we doing?
We are about to call forth
the Kashoh‐Zanmai.
[Mephisto thinking]
My goodness, a blue Ucchusma!
To exploit
the Koma Sword's potential,
one must possess the blade
with a Buddhist fire demon,
whose lord is Fudo.
Even though Okumura's
demon heart also resides
in the blade,
its power is intact.
This is not what I expected,
but it's entertaining
nonetheless.
The Kashoh‐Zanmai
will incinerate
everything in this world.
With the addition
of your demonic flame,
it shall purify the Impure King,
along with every living thing
on this mountain.
Wait. Purify?
Like burn the whole mountain?
Dude, there's a lot
of people up here.
What of it?
They are of no importance.
Those who set foot
in the Impure King's castle
or were touched by his minions
have all been contaminated.
They must all be cleansed
without exception,
for the Impure King
can regenerate
from even the tiniest speck.
‐Come!
‐Hold on!
[Impure King roars]
[Rin thinking] There's no time
to think about it.
I have to kill that thing
and not hurt anyone else!
But... how?
Screw it, I gotta try!
You can no longer afford
to dawdle.
Begin!
[both chanting spell]
‐[Ucchusma] Good!
‐[Rin] No way!
[Rin] The words are just
in my head.
[Rin chants spell]
[roars]
[Ucchusma] Chant the sutra
and release it!
[chanting sutra]
[Impure King groans]
[chuckles]
[straining]
Now... what?
[Ucchusma] Why do you hesitate?
Pour more power into it!
[Rin] But... if I do that,
then...
I'm the one
that's gonna get torched!
[panting]
It's no use!
This darn fungus is growing
faster than I can handle!
The only thing to do
is pull Ms. Kamiki out.
‐[Izumo straining]
‐Hey, Nee!
Could you please give me
a boost up to her?
[Nee roars]
‐[Nee] Nee!
‐[Shiemi gasps]
[Shiemi] Nee!
Would you stop? Can't you tell
you're totally exhausted?
You used your demon too much!
You'll die!
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
I hate your guts.
Get away from me!
Leave me alone!
Hmm‐mm. I won't.
You don't have to like me
if you don't want to.
[Shiemi straining]
It doesn't matter!
[Shiemi thinking] That's right,
it doesn't matter.
And I'm OK with that.
Ugggh!
Hey. Hey! Shiemi.
Are you OK, are you alive?
Yep.
Oh, man.
Dummy!
I swear, you're so, so...
You can hate me
all you want, Ms. Kamiki,
'cause even if you do,
I still like you.
We... We don't have the time
to sit here and chat. Come on!
We have to get
the Master down the mount...
‐[rumbling]
‐...tain.
[priest] Hey, what's with
that blue light?
That's... Kashoh‐Zanmai?
Only that one's way beyond
what I summoned.
Then who's summoning that one?
Hey, wait!
[Yukio thinking] No!
This can't be happening.
[Rin thinking] These flames
feel like they're
swallowing me!
[straining]
[harshly] Yes!
All my life
I had to hold my power back
and be cool with it!
[straining]
No, stop!
Well, screw that!
I'm free now!
And I'm gonna destroy
everything!
I'm a demon that's gonna
burn the world to ashes!
That's who I really am!
[straining]
I'm not afraid.
‐[Rin gasps]
‐[Rin thinking] Shiemi!
Look, there's not a single burn
anywhere on me.
You made sure of that.
[Rin thinking] Yeah.
Everyone's got my back.
They believe in me.
I can't let 'em down.
[priests screaming]
‐What the...
‐[priests yelling]
[Yaozo] Take cover!
[Izumo] Blue flames?
Oh, my God,
let's get out of here!
Don't worry.
We won't get burned.
What? Are you crazy?
We totally will.
[shrieks]
[Shiemi thinking] I knew it.
They're warm.
Rin.
Huh? Hey, wait.
What the...
The only thing the flames
are burning is the fungus.
I don't understand.
Oh!
[Renzo] Look! The Impure King
globbies are melting!
I can see the ground again.
The path's clear.
Let's go back up, Koneko!
Right!
Wait! Boys, get back here!
[Uwabami] I'm going
back up, too.
‐Whoever's able, follow me.
‐[priests] Yes, sir!
[Mephisto] Magnificent!
Now that is
a ceremonial bonfire!
[chuckles]
Witness the birth
of the Blue Exorcist,
a creature designed
to kill its own kind.
[chuckles]
[Mephisto laughing hysterically]
The cleansing is complete.
I shall now depart.
Hmm.
I am still not sure
which you are, human...
or demon.
There will come a day
when you must choose.
And you will.
Hey, Suguro.
You OK?
Yeah.
I'm fine, but what happened?
See for yourself.
Okumura.
[Rin] Suguro. Shura. I...
[breathing erratically]
I... I did it!
I controlled my flames!
[both] Huh?
I still gotta fine‐tune
a couple things,
but I can decide what gets burnt
and what don't now.
[giggles]
[Konekomaru] Hey, Okumura!
‐Bon!
‐[Suguro] Koneko! Shima!
[Suguro] You're OK.
Konekomaru!
Dude, you won't believe it!
I can control my power!
I made my flames
burn the Impure King all up
and nothing else!
Well, that explains it.
Man, it was super weird
when your flames hit us.
We were covered in 'em,
but we didn't feel nothin'.
Didn't even tingle.
[Yaozo] Those blue flames
of yours cleansed
everything they touched,
everyone who was afflicted
by the miasma, even me.
Thank you for saving everyone.
Your powers are truly amazing.
[Rin] Aww, shucks!
Keep talking like that
and I'm gonna start blushing.
[chuckles]
[sobbing]
Okumura, I was wrong.
Thank you.
And please forgive me.
[gasp] Why are you crying?!
Did I scare you again?
Nah, dude, he keeps his feelings
bottled up inside,
then lets them rip...
the usual.
[gasp] Holy hell!
How'd you make it out alive?
I already got used
to you being gone.
You know I'm kidding.
[Suguro] Sorry if I
made you worry.
[chuckles] Worry about you?
Never.
[Yukio] Rin!
[panting]
Oh, hey, Yukio!
I was wondering where you were.
[Yukio] Shura.
What is my brother doing here?
Who let him out of his cell?
Remember my apology from before?
That's for this.
‐[growling]
‐[Rin] See, Yukio?
I saved everybody here
like a freakin' boss!
Bet your head's spinnin' now,
ain't it?
[Rin laughs loudly]
Soon I'll leave you behind.
Eat my dust.
You idiot! Do you understand
the mess you're in?
Yeah, I understand.
Don't you worry.
I get it.
Sure, I'm the spawn of Satan.
I can't escape that or my power.
I've always been afraid of it,
of facing it, accepting it.
But now, now I understand
how wrong I was.
Take a good look.
This is me, Yukio,
this is who I am.
[groaning]
If I'm not cool with myself...
I'm not gonna get anywhere.
Yukio, we're brothers.
I need you to be cool...
with me too.
‐[Rin collapses]
‐[Yukio] Rin!
[Suguro] Okumura!
Dad. Hey, Dad, I don't know what
I'm supposed to do from now on.
Do you know?
Seriously? You're gonna have to
work that out for yourself.
[grown‐up Rin] What the hell
did you save me for?
[Rin] Yukio, I need
to talk to you.
It can wait for now.
But soon.