[Todo] Your father always
treated your brother
like he was special.
And how did he treat you?
I'm sure he was strict
and made you work extra hard
so you could become
an Exorcist like him.
Or maybe he raised you that way
to serve another purpose:
to protect his favorite son!
No! Becoming an Exorcist
was my choice!
Dad and Rin had nothing
to do with it!
[chuckles]
You're not even aiming!
It's obvious you're upset.
I don't blame you.
I'm sure the thought's crossed
your mind many times,
even now:
why do you have to be the one
to protect Rin?
It must feel awful,
especially since he doesn't
know how much you've suffered.
It's OK to say it's not fair.
It's OK to say you can't
stand this anymore.
Yeah‐ah‐ah‐ah!
This is so rad!
‐Whoooo!
‐We're gonna die!
[chuckles]
It's OK to say
you hate your brother.
And you do, don't you?
[Uverworld singing
"Itteki No Eikyou" in Japanese]
Are you done playing
your head games yet?
Huh! You really
know how to keep your cool!
That's one way to avoid
confronting your feelings.
I bet you've done it
all your life, haven't you?
[Yukio] I...
When I was little.
[young Yukio] Whoa! A puppy!
[laughter]
[father] Uh... Boys?
What you got there?
Aw, come on, Dad,
why can't we keep him?!
[sniffling]
[Rin] Bye!
Take good care of him!
[Yukio] I looked up to Rin.
But...
‐[boys jeering Yukio]
‐[boy] Loser!
‐[Rin] Stop it!
‐[boy 1] It's Rin!
[boy 2] Bail!
[boys laughing]
You OK?
I don't need your help!
‐What's with you?
‐I don't need you to save me!
Those dicks were
gonna beat you up!
[Yukio] At the same time, I...
You need this?
...the truth is, I...
[Rin laughing]
Thanks for the blanket, Yukio.
No, Rin's the one who...
[Rin laughing]
[Yukio] I was always...
always...
resentful!
[Todo] Oh, dear.
Are you OK over there?
Don't tell me
I wore you out!
Huh?
What's happening?
Corycia. Melainah.
Cleodora. Cleochareia.
Bateia.
Drosera. Solaia. Periboea.
[Todo] Now that was clever.
And here I thought I was faster
than your aim.
But you missed on purpose.
You were using your bullets
to form a naiad
summoning circle.
‐[naiads giggling]
‐You are quite gifted.
[Shura] Be honest with yourself
before it's too late.
The truth is, I love
my brother... and hate him.
But what I hate more...
is how weak
and helpless I used to be.
In the end, the person I hate
the most is myself!
Naiad Fylaki!
‐[naiads giggling]
‐[Todo choking]
[Kuro] It attacks
whenever I try to land!
It might look like a castle,
but it's a mountain demon,
all right!
[Karura] We must
center the barrier.
but I do not see a clear spot
to place the Earth sign.
Even if there was,
I wouldn't have the time
I need to chant the spell!
[Rin] Kuro! We need to find
a safe spot to set up!
‐Keep an eye out for one!
‐[Kuro] I'm looking!
I'm looking!
Oh, man.
That spore sac's huge!
[thinking] I only heard
the barrier spell once.
I don't even know if
I got the whole thing
memorized right!
Even if I do and I get
the barrier up,
how are we gonna kill
that thing?
‐[stomach groans]
‐Aaah!
Sorry about that,
but I didn't eat dinner
and now I'm starving!
Is it just me or does that thing
look like a giant meat bun?
[Suguro] How can you be so calm,
when everything around us
is tryin' to get us?!
I'm totally freakin' out
back here!
[Rin] That's not my fault!
Winner sits up front!
And go!
You lost fair and square, homie!
I'm not talkin'
about that, you dumbass!
I'm talkin' about how,
if you can't draw that sword,
you're just a strong kid
waving a stick around.
Aren't you worried about that?!
[Kuro] Rin!
There's a spot down there!
Hold on!
This rock is the only place
that's not covered!
[Rin] Welp... this is as good
a place to die as any.
I knew it!
You don't think we're gonna
make it out alive, either.
What? No, just tryin'
to sound cool!
Don't worry! And try not
to shit yer pants, big guy.
‐Why, you...
‐Dude.
Right now, everyone's doing
whatever they can to stop this.
No way are we gonna
let 'em down!
So get that barrier up and quit
actin' like a whiny princess!
Who're you callin' a princess?
You wanna get yer ass beat?!
Hey, I'm just tellin' it
how I see it!
So hitch up yer skirt
and get to chanting,
you macho princess, you!
You son of a...
I don't need you to tell me
what to do.
Good, I'm counting
on you, babe.
[Rin] We can beat this, Suguro!
♪ It's time for me... ♪
‐Giddyap! Let's ride, Kuro!
‐Hey, I'm not a horse!
[Suguro] He's a doofus.
But he's not an idiot.
Deep down I know that.
[chanting]
He's just like my dad,
always acting like a lone wolf.
Never asking for help
when he needs it.
That's my problem with him.
[chanting]
And it pisses me off!
Ryuji Suguro, by your request,
I shall grant your spell.
[bird screeches]
[onlookers gasp]
What is that?
That's a fire barrier.
But who cast it?
Oh, my, what a spectacular
fireworks display.
Right on, Suguro!
That's the coolest thing
you've done yet.
It's very cool, Suguro.
[Suguro] I'm just glad I got
the barrier up.
[Yukio] I've never
done that before.
I didn't think it would be
this draining.
[Todo laughs]
I'm impressed.
You're not even a Tamer meister.
And yet somehow you have
the skill to summon
all these naiads.
You need more practice, though.
[Yukio groans]
[Todo] Well, it was nice
chatting with you.
Honestly, I didn't expect
you'd be so interesting.
But unfortunately I'm going
to have to kill you now.
Oh, but first, have you ever
wondered how long it takes
for a body to turn to ash?
I know I have, so how about
we time it and see, eh?
[Yukio] Rin!
Yukio?
[Suguro] Hey, watch it!
[Rin groans] Back off!
I hate to say it but I think
we really pissed it off.
I'll say! It looks
like it'll pop any second!
[Rin] Bet that's why the little
blobs are moving faster!
Come get some, you bastards!
He beat them back,
but they just keep coming!
[Karura] Ryuji.
Do not break the Earth sign.
If you do, the barrier will
break with it.
You don't have to remind me,
I know what to do!
I'll die before I break it!
[Rin laughs]
Don't bust
a blood vessel, Princess!
Would you quit callin' me that?!
Then quit bein' a spazz
or you'll end up passin' out.
[Konekomaru] Bon got the barrier
up around the sporangium!
We need to get to the others
before it explodes!
[chuckles] I'm all for it, but
you see what's in front of us?
We can't go that way
'cuz the goo's
totally blockin' the path.
Hmm?
Aaah!
[groaning] Yaaa!
Oh, crap!
[Yaozo] Renzo.
This was my k'rik.
‐How did you get up there?
‐How do you think?! Come on!
Great idea.
That stuff's related to Rot,
so it hates fire.
If we use the torch
to keep it away,
we can get down the path.
‐Konekomaru, it's hopeless.
‐Why?
Just think about it
for a second.
That torch ain't gonna last
the whole way down.
Let's bail.
Tryin' to get to the others
is suicide, so let's just run!
Bon and the others will
understand.
In a situation like this,
who can blame us?
Right?
You're kidding.
Our classmates are down there.
Our family's down there
fighting.
How dare you think it's OK
to just run away!
Well, I won't.
If I ran away,
I could never look anyone
from Myoda in the eye again.
‐[Renzo sighs]
‐[Renzo] Not you too.
Everyone's always talking about
honor and responsibility,
family this and Myoda that.
I'm sick of hearing it.
If you think any of that stuff's
worth dying for, it isn't.
How can you talk like that,
at a time like this?!
'Cause none of it matters
if you're dead!
I'm outta here.
‐Wait, you're not serious.
‐Yep, I'm not that noble.
Or stupid.
If you don't wanna come, fine.
I'll just go by myself.
You coward!
[miasma rumbling]
[thinking] Man! Koneko, Bon,
Dad and my brothers.
They're all the same.
Renzo, our big brother died
because he was trying
to protect you and Bon.
Never forget Takezo.
He saved your life,
so live it in a way
that would make him proud.
[Renzo] So what?
Whenever I'm in trouble,
I think about what Takezo would
do if he were in my shoes.
Take's the pride
of our family, dude.
[Renzo] I don't
even remember him.
This was my k'rik
and now I'm giving it to you.
‐Why?
‐I'm passing it on to you
because you're a man now.
You represent the Shimas,
so protect Bon and Konekomaru.
[Renzo thinking]
Too much responsibility,
too much hassle.
Myoda, family, honor.
I wish all of it
would just disappear!
[Konekomaru reciting chant]
[straining]
‐[Konekomaru screams]
‐[Renzo sighs]
[Renzo thinking] If I could
put it all behind me,
life would be way easier.
What the...
You set my k'rik on fire!
No way. Master Yaozo must
have summoned Ucchusma.
I'll chant a mantra
to make the flames stronger.
You keep that stuff off me
until I finish.
Thanks a lot, man.
I come back to save you
and now I'm your bodyguard?
[Konekomaru] I know, I'm sorry.
And I'm also sorry
I called you a coward.
Aah, just hurry up, already.
[Shiemi] Do you hear that?
I think the sporangium
is about to blow up.
We can't stay here.
Uke! Mike!
‐Oh, honestly.
‐What a slave driver.
‐Come forth, kin of Ukemochi!
‐Come forth, kin of Miketsu.
[creatures screeching]
[creatures] Heave‐ho!
[Shiemi] Oh, my gosh,
they're so cute!
We can't carry him,
but these little guys can.
They're teeny
but they sure are strong.
Hang on, is this how you got
the Peg Lantern back to camp?
Excuse me, I'm trying to
concentrate, so stop talking.
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
[Izumo thinking]
Izumo, what are you doing here?
You dummy.
Why did you have to help
when you could have said no?
I must have a screw loose
somewhere.
I haven't been myself
since I met these losers.
Oh, well, I gave my word,
so that's that.
I just hope we can
make it out of this alive.
Ms. Kamiki,
you're doing awesome,
and if I can do anything
to help, just let me know.
[Izumo thinking] God, could she
be any more annoying?
For your information, I don't
need or want your help.
You're too weak!
Be a good girl, shut up,
and let me protect you!
[gasps]
‐[Izumo screams]
‐Ms. Kamiki!
‐[Shiemi] Oh, no!
‐Forget about me.
Uke, Mike, get Master Tatsuma
away from here!
Wonderful.
This is what we get
for serving an amateur.
Damn it!
[thinking] Come on,
do something! Think!
You can't die now.
Don't stand there.
Run, you idiot!
[Shiemi] No, I won't!
I can't just leave you here
like this!
What? Are you crazy?
I'm just going to slow you down,
so get going!
‐[miniature explosions]
‐Uke, Mike!
Master Tatsuma!
[Izumo groaning]
[Shiemi thinking]
I have to do something.
Nee, if you can hear me,
come out!
[Izumo groaning]
If you don't come out now,
what's the point in having you?!
I don't wanna be weak.
Please, come out!
We have to save her.
I can't leave her here alone!
Please come out!
I want us all back together!
Come out!
Nee!
Nee! You came back.
I really need your help
right now.
Nee! Nee! Nee!
OK, first we gotta save
Ms. Kamiki!
Nee! Nee!
The fungus is gonna eat
your plants,
so you're gonna have to sprout
twice as many, OK?
Neeeee!
Oh, wow!
That's amazing, Nee!
You're growing so fast.
[Izumo] She's making
her greenman grow so big.
Ms. Kamiki, hey,
we'll save you, don't worry.
OK, Nee, go for it!
[Nee] Yaaaa!
[popping]
Arrrrgh!
I don't think so!
Okumura!
[Kuro screeches]
[Rin] Kuro!
There's no stopping this thing!
[Suguro] Okumura, behind you!
I got it!
[groaning]
I got it.
[priest] It's gonna burst.
[chanting]
Huh!
Oh, no.
[explosion]
[groaning]
[Yukio] I'm going to die.
No, no!
[Todo gasps]
What?
Why is everything blue?
What's going on?
What happened to... my eyes?
[Todo] Your eyes...
they changed.
How strange.
My instincts kicked in
and made me jump clear of you.
I said you were
interesting before.
It seems that was quite
the understatement.
[Yukio] What...
What are you...
[panting]
Those eyes, they don't
belong to you, do they?
Argggh!
Oh, my, you again.
You're so persistent.
How in the world
did you know I was here?
Mr. Shima.
When you're
showing off your flames,
you're easy to find.
You rotten bastard!
J‐Juzo.
[chuckles]
You've ruined everything
that was important to me,
and when I get done...
[sword clangs]
there won't even be ash
left of you!
[Rin Akatsuki singing
"Kono Te De" in Japanese]
[Rin] What was the point
in saving someone like me?