The Glacies Exile...
I can't hear it any longer.
No.
Dio, the Exiles were never
meant to be used for fighting.
That's true.
And yet... Exiles have always
been at the center of our wars.
In a place far
beyond these skies...
we fought over an Exile
ourselves... didn't we?
Second Adjournment.
Prester... the artificial
land we called home...
was divided by two nations
that were constantly at war.
On one side was Anatoray.
On the other was Disith...
The Guild acted as arbitrator
between the lands.
The Grand Stream separated
the two nations,
and within its turbulent
winds was an Exile,
awaiting the appointed time.
The Exile was a colony ship
brought by the first settlers,
meant to return us to our
homeland.
But that knowledge had
long ago been lost,
and we instead believed it
possessed god-like power.
And it was me, Alvis Hamilton,
who was the key to that Exile.
The Guild wanted to use
it for world domination,
and I was no longer
safe... so I escaped.
I'd like you...
to take my mission.
It's seven stars?!
The cargo...
I entrust her to you.
This girl...?
I, Claus Valca...
Vanship pilot,
hereby take over...
Ralph Wednesday's
divine mission.
I got a little present for ya...
...you monster!
Well then...
My name is Claus...
and this is Lavie.
So um... while you
were still sleeping,
we were asked to
take over the job.
They were Vanship pilots...
Two young sky couriers.
And I loved them both...
Well, I was a little bit
scared of Lavie at first...
but the tasty sandwiches
that she made
won me over before long.
Guita...
Guita... She's not
coming back... is she?
I'm sorry.
Let go! Let go of her...!
Claus!
I was finally delivered to
a ship called the Silvana,
and its Captain, Alex Row...
I was afraid I might never
see Claus and Lavie again.
Lord Dio, the preparations
are complete.
Shortly thereafter...
we arrived at the scene.
Lord Dio.
Luciola...
don't you think that dead
bodies are very intriguing?
Who... is this?
Of all the pilots in
this dull battlefield...
Immelman was the only
one who seemed to shine.
I'm going to give you
some flying lessons,
so try to pay attention.
Don't you think you're
getting a little close?
I'm afraid you may not realize
whom you're talking to...
You may refer to me
as Professor Dio.
Time is up.
Oh, very well then.
I hope we get to do
this again soon.
Our next encounter came
sooner than I thought...
We met in Horizon Cave...
for an eight-hour long
Vanship endurance race.
Now, Claus...! Max the output!
Gotcha!
Lord Dio--
Luciola, we're going to lose!
We can't go any
faster, Lord Dio...
At the last pit stop
we filled up our--
Then get out,
Luciola! Right now!
Come on, floor it!
We did it!
Did you win?
Yeah.
They're making a party!
A party sounds wonderful!
I trailed Immelman and wound
up a prisoner on the Silvana.
But... that was
my plan all along.
Right... I'm a prisoner of war.
It's nearly dawn.
I hate you.
Why's that?
'Cause you're weird.
You think so?
Yeah, for one thing you call
Claus by a weird name.
Yes, but Immelman is Immelman.
Claus is just Claus!
And you are Alvis.
How do you know about me?
I know a lot about you.
I'll recite you a little poem.
A poem?
What poem?
What lies deep within the
furthest reaches of the skies?
This is... amazing!
Al!
That which will guide the lost
child back to her mother's arms.
Exile...
Last Exile.
I realized that Alvis
and the four Mysterion
were required to
activate the Exile.
How many of them do
you know, Captain...? Two?
No, I've got it... Three.
And what was Alex's objective?
It was simple...
He wished to obtain an Exile...
change the world...
and do whatever it would take to
bring down the Maestro Delphine.
--Lord Dio! Please calm down!
--She's coming for me...!
Delphine's found me!
Shoot it down at once!
I know that she's on board...!
The Maestro is there!
Delphine... My older sister.
Happy birthday to you, Dio!
This has gotta be the best
water I've ever had...
It's better if you savor it.
Thanks a lot.
These are from me. I hope
they're not too beat up for ya.
Immelman!
There's cake, too!
Try some, Dio!
It was because of their
kindness and generosity
that I realized how wonderful
a birthday could be...
--This is wonderful!
--However...
Please...!
I would soon face
the Trial of Agoon,
the Guild's coming
of age ceremony.
Luciola! He'll save
me--Luciola...! Luciola!
They dragged me back home...
and shattered my
grasp on reality.
Now... let the trial... begin!
Dio is absolutely magnificent.
Alvis, you're going to
be the star of the show.
I'm here now... I'm right here.
Excellent, let's begin with
House Dagobert's Mysterion.
Dagobert, the waves that
flow and dye the land gold.
The blessed breath,
the nurturing breath of life.
A land... of wheat.
Having acquired me
and the Mysterion...
Delphine now had the tools to
take possession of the Exile.
Dio's mind never
returned to normal,
even after it was all over.
Nonetheless...
Luciola helped Claus, Dio and me
escape from Delphine's ship...
Luciola...! What can you
accomplish by yourself?
I will remove those who try
to bring harm to Lord Dio.
I smiled like a simpleton...
laughed like a mad man, who'd
been robbed of his memories.
Very well done, Luciola.
I'll give you a reward.
Set Lord Dio free.
Go ahead... Take it.
I want you to tell me why you
let my precious Dio escape.
I merely--
It's odd... because you two
aren't even friends.
What do you mean
to Dio, Luciola?
So is it good?
Mm-Hm.
If you like how something tastes
it should show on your face!
My face?
Listen... Luciola, you and me
are going to be friends!
Because...
He is my--he is my friend
and I won't betray him.
Is that so?
Wonderful!
How beautiful... Luciola!
Throttle off... check.
Verify... check.
All clear.
Starting engine.
Everybody ready?
Good luck, Claus.
May fair winds be with you.
After reuniting with Lavie,
the three of us headed
back to the Grand Stream.
This time... we would take back
the Exile from Delphine.
It was already a hard task,
but a still-confused
Dio trailing us
only made things worse.
Bearing, 1 o'clock...!
Rainbirds!
I can see the finish line!
We're gonna lose, Luciola!
Can't we go any faster?!
Maybe you should just
jump out, Luciola!
We won!
We did it!
We really did! We won!
We beat Immelman! Luciola!
Luciola?
Because I said to jump out...?
Just because I told you
to jump out...?! Luciola!
I'm sorry, Claus! I don't
know what our heading is!
Clear a path for our Empress!
All ships commence fire at will!
Exile keeps sending
out more tentacles...!
I can't count them all!
Timed fuse torpedoes
engage, full spread!
Fire!
Open main turrets 1 through 3!
The target is the Urbanus!
All hands, make for the
ship's bow! Here she comes!
Open fire!
Take course elevation
to 20 degrees!.
Continue forward...
at flank speed!
Majesty...!
Give the Maestro hell!
Diminishing-caliber,
heavy antiaircraft cannon!
Commence fire!
I heard the Captain's voice
inside Delphine's ship!
To the sky...
Claus...! Bearing... 2 o'clock!
I'm gonna hit the booster!
Punch it!
The Grand Stream...
We crossed it.
Lavie...
What's this?
This must be... Disith...
Ok, Claus, you're gonna have
to take me to Exile now.
You got it, let's go.
Lavie!
Claus...
You did it...
You crossed the Grand Stream.
It's up to you.
What lies in the furthest
reaches of the sky?
That which guides a lost
child back to her mother...
Exile.
Waves that flow...
and dye the land gold.
A land full of grain...
blessed by the breath
that nurtures life.
The path the angels
descend upon.
The path of great winds.
The Grand Stream.
What lies in the furthest
reaches of one's memory?
The place where all are born...
and all will return.
A blue star.
Hey! Look, they're back!
We swore to make a new world...
A world without Anatoray...
or Disith... or The Guild.
A world of peace, where we
could live without conflict.
And yet we are at
war once again...
No matter where I go, I'll
always be targeted and used...
Those I care about get hurt...
I don't think I can
take it anymore.
Alvis.
I know it's been rough on you,
but you know why we're here...
Because everyone
has come together.
My life... is the same as yours.
We live on... we keep going...
even when it's hard.
Dio!
Let's go... Run!
Wake up, sleepyhead!
Come on... It's lunch time!
It's going to be all right, Al.
I promised Immelman...
that I would keep you safe.