I'm sorry, Father...
Luscinia!
I swear... you will pay for
this!
If it's your wish to kill me,
Princess, by all means, do so.
But before you pull the trigger,
you should know that killing me
now will not end the war...
Indeed, it would only
lead to greater chaos
and more bloodshed...
A fierce power
struggle would begin
for the title of
Federation Premier.
One death always
leads to another...
Humanity does not yet
know how to break
its perpetual chain of revenge.
But, Princess...
If you are confident
that your rule
would establish peace for all...
Then do it.
Save this forsaken
world in my place...
so the dream may live.
Queening Square.
Oh, Lily...
How could I have been
so blind to everything...?
I didn't know what
you were doing...
or the burden you
were forced to bear.
How long have you had to endure
the dreadful weight
of this knowledge...?
The memories you
inherit as a "Key."
People everywhere will always
repeat their mistakes...
will always fall to despair.
Always... No matter what...
It's inevitable...
Even knowing that,
you sacrificed yourself...
You suffered so that
others could be saved.
I'm so stupid.
I didn't understand anything...
I thought if we could
all just get along
then all the hatred and
anger would disappear...
and the whole world
would finally be at peace.
[in Russian]
I am sorry for what
happened to Liliana.
With her, hope for
a truce died as well...
I deeply regret that this is so.
You fully expected something
like this would happen
from the very beginning,
didn't you?
You only went along
with the truce so easily
because you knew it was
gonna fall apart again!
This was honestly not how I
had hoped things would end...
I had the same wish as you...
...after all this time... that
the world had found true peace.
However...
I didn't confuse
hope with reality...
...so, I knew...
peace was not to be.
Please, look after
Princess Millia...
I know it's what
Liliana would wish.
If you really
wanted peace so badly,
then why did you
go and start a war?!
Because I felt
it was necessary...
What other reason
can I possibly give?
Think on that...
You should do what you
feel is necessary, as well.
We cannot stop now,
otherwise Liliana's sacrifice
will have been in vain.
Indeed... This is our
final opportunity to atone
for the sin of surviving
that day ten years ago.
Very well... proceed as planned.
Should one
of us falter or fall...
...the other will
continue to the end.
The first and second fleets
are departing already?
That seems awful quick.
They didn't
inform us about this.
Have the Second Fleet
take the lead.
Meanwhile, we will see
to guarding the rear
and keeping the
volunteer forces in check...
Should they strike,
counterattack at once.
Aye, Sir!
It appears the Urbanus
won't arrive for
a few more days yet, Captain.
Getting a late start...
This truce is
messier than expected...
Dio, what would you do?
Not sure, whatever happens,
happens, right?
This is the Bridge, go ahead.
All of Luscinia's fleets
are on the move...
No advance notice or
request for clearan--!
Sh-Shouldn't we stop them?
We haven't been given
an attack order yet!
If we let them go now,
Luscinia will win!
So the truce has
fallen apart already.
Hold fire...
Do not attack until we've
learned their true intentions...
Where's Orang?
He's on his way to
the Admirari, General.
Get the fleet ready
to sail now...
To sail... but not
to fire, understood?
Aye-aye!
Luscinia... You won't
even mourn her properly?
Vasant!
What's happened?
Everything's fine...
I can assure you,
there is nothing
to be concerned about,
Your Majesty.
Although... things may be
getting a bit hectic soon...
...so it might be best if you
would move to a different sh--
No!
Please, Vasant...!
Just tell me what's really
happening out there...!
I know I'm still young...
...and I know I might
not understand it all...
...but I need to know!
I'm the Augusta...! I'll order
you to tell me if I have to!
Please, Your Majesty I--
I can't stand it...!
My people are out there
getting hurt and dying,
and I'm waiting here,
left in the dark...! Tell me!
Please accept my deepest
apologies, Majesty.
Yes, of course...
Gloria, Augusta...
I'm at your mercy...
From now on, I will--
I'm certain you know why
I'm here... Come, Augusta.
Don't move...! Guards,
in here...! Stop him!
Why fight?
Or have you
forgotten what I am...?
Surely you haven't.
Come with me, dear Augusta.
Luscinia!
Augusta... I'm sorry.
Last Exile.
Luscinia's done what?!
All of his fleets
are on the move...
They're ignoring every signal
our fleet sends to them.
What about Vasant...?
Has she issued any orders yet?
No, none at all.
We've lost contact with her.
Everything's so chaotic...
We have no idea what's going on!
This way!
Hurry!
(in Russian)
It's looking like we have to go
on the run again for a while...
Sorry... How are you...? Okay?
Never mind about me...
Are you hurt?
Dio!
Stay down, Al!
Luscinia...
Thank you, Al...
You're a life-saver.
But Dio, I didn't--
What do you mean?
I have succeeded in rescuing our
beloved leader from
the traitor scum...
Now, fly her flag!
We can expect
their immediate pursuit...
I'll let you deal with that...
I will travel north with the
Augusta as previously planned.
Have a Vanship ready.
Aye, sir!
I believe that this truly will
be the decisive battle...
After this, the world will
finally know peace...
Just as Farahnaz had wished.
Indeed... As soon
as this battle is over,
I intend to retire
from active service...
I'll let Augusta
Sara and the
youngsters take
care of the rest.
Admiral, you have
my sincerest gratitude.
No 'thank you's' yet, Premier...
It's too soon...
Wait until this is over.
Indeed.
Alauda...
When the premier returns,
he will bring with him
the power to make world
peace a reality at last.
These traitors sought
to corrupt the Augusta...
Give them the justice they
deserve...! Gloria, Augusta!
Gloria, Augusta!
The--the Impetus is
flying the Augusta's flag!
Again, Luscinia...?
How many times must you
act in defiance of
our leader's wishes...?
We must rescue the
Augusta...! Full speed ahead!
This is horrible.
I'm gonna go, too...!
I'll get Sara to safety!
Good, I will remain here and try
to get things back in order...
At the least, we need to
establish the chain of command.
Millia!
I'm really sorry...
I should've thought
more about how
other people felt
during all this.
Dyan's need for revenge...
Your intense suffering...
I couldn't understand it...
Worse... I never even tried.
I forced all of my
dreams onto you...
...even though you were
carrying so much already.
Just like with Dyan.
I wasn't thinking...
All I could see was what
I wanted to happen...
Another Grand Race was
all that mattered to me.
I never even really thought
about how we could do it...
I guess I just
figured it would all
magically come together somehow.
Like there was nothing
more to it than that.
So, it's not much...
but I'm sorry...
I had to at least tell you that.
Wait!
I should have given
it back sooner.
Fam...
It's only because of you, that
I was able to make it this far.
Your dream gave me the hope
I needed to continue trying...
Without it, I would've
given up long ago...
I would've abandoned my own
dream of rebuilding my kingdom.
We'll do it... We'll have
a Grand Race... I promise!
Millia...
Hey, don't forget about me,
we're all in this together...
No matter what
the future might hold,
we'll never let go of our dream!
That's right!
All ships, change formation!
Obliterate the
treacherous enemy!
Are you still so
determined to fight
against the dream
of true peace?!
Where is she?
What happened to Vasant?
I humbly welcome your return to
the Grand Exile... Maestro Sara.
What do you mean?
I do this in order
to save the world...
...to make Augusta Farahnaz's
peaceful dream
a reality at last.
That which slumbers
deeply in the land of snow...
...a faint and distant promise
which guides those who are lost.
A vast ocean
brimming with stars...
The far-reaching path of
those who have departed.
The dream delivered
only by the angels of war...
...a beacon... a shining
symbol of hope and life...
The Grand Exile.
At the far end of the world...
lie snow-white wings...
...which surpass everything
in their greatness.
These wretches must pay for
desecrating the
Augusta's dream...!
Ours is a just cause!
We must fight in
the name of the Augusta...!
As always, we are
her obedient swords!
Do not let a
single ship through.
All ships, keep the pressure on!
Sara...!
Let us go forth...
...abandoning the
ancient land of strife...
Seeking bountiful skies
and everlasting seas.
Pray for good tailwinds to carry
the wings of the beloved child
bound for a new world.
Fly strong... Fly high.
Claudia Unit down!
Helm inoperable!
Losing altitude quickly!
Target the Third Fleet's
flagship, the Admirari...!
Let's put an end to them,
once and for all!
Fire!
What the... heck is--
Stop fussing, I'll be fine...
Are the others all right?
Yes, sir.
Your Majesty.
We will arrive at the
skirmish point shortly.
Whatever we may face,
failure in this battle
is not an option.
Understood! I shall do
everything in my power
to ensure a favorable outcome.
All forces,
Type 1 battle stations!
All ships, full speed ahead!
Roger.
Vince...
Yes?
These people we're
about to fight for...
...do they even know who we are?
Uh.. All hands to
Type 1 battle stations!
All ships, full speed ahead!