Admiral Sadri says that he
agrees to the cease-fire.
Thank you!
Aw, it was nothing!
[in Russian]
Transposition.
Thank you for overseeing
things in my absence.
I accepted the truce without
first consulting you...
I hope that I was
not out of line.
No, you made the proper
decision, Admiral...
I commend your handling of
the battle for Boreas...
Overall, a job very well done.
Thank you, sir...
but you are too kind.
Luscinia... I am so glad
that you've returned.
Gloria, Augusta...
I am at your mercy.
A great deal of blood has been
shed in the recent fighting...
For this I bear full
responsibility...
I offer my deepest apologies
to the people of Ades
and all foreign lands.
Vasant... Luscinia.
I am happy to see you
standing before me
peacefully once more...
Happier than you know.
Please, accept my
apologies, Augusta...
I have caused pain
to Your Majesty...
For that... I am
filled with shame.
Although, I had no choice...
I am sorry, but I could
not stand idly by
and allow Luscinia's heinous
crimes to continue...
Before this truce is final, I
demand the Premier be replaced.
How dare you...?!
You are the treasonous
one here, Vasant...
For what you've done, I demand
you face a court-martial.
You were the one who fired on
the Augusta's flag, Kayvan...
That is the action of a traitor.
We were rescuing the Augusta
from a disloyal general.
Disloyal?!
You heard me, you turned
your back on the Ades cause...
when you willingly
supported the repatriates!
The Ades cause...?
The Federation's only
cause now appears to be
the total destruction of other
lands...!
The victims are many...
Turan, Glacies, and
Anatoray, as well.
Tell them about your "cause."
I am happy to.
Our objective is quite simple...
We wish to see this
world's limited resources
passed on to the
next generation.
The ruler of Turan herself
understands what must be done.
Yes, he speaks the truth...
Luscinia's cause is a just one.
And the kingdom of
Turan supports it.
I am Millia il Velch
Cutrettola Turan...
and I ask to speak.
Oh! I'm so sorry...
I'll bring a replacement
straight away.
What is security like?
Tighter than expected.
I see...
Lily, you are unfit
to lead our kingdom.
Listen to the princess speak...
I have no doubt that she will
sympathize with our cause...
Do whatever it
takes to bring her.
It shall be done.
Do not speak of what you
do not understand, Millia...
We must consider ourselves first
as inhabitants of this world
and then as Turanians.
Is that how you justify
using the Exile
to murder thousands
of innocents?
This world we live on
is far too small...
It lacks adequate
space and resources
to provide for everyone.
That may be true...
but it doesn't give you
the right to choose
who lives and dies.
That decision is
not yours to make.
In other words...
Princess Liliana was
a willing accomplice
to the crimes committed
by Premier Luscinia...
And, as such,
she has demonstrated
her unworthiness to claim
leadership of Turan...
Is that what you're trying
to say, Princess Millia?
Uh, yes... Yes, that's right!
Lily, you have acted in
defiance of our people's will!
Can you not see that?!
She cannot...
Your plea has fallen on
deaf ears, Princess Millia...
Our requirements
are as follows...
Premier Luscinia
must be replaced
and stripped of all titles...
and Liliana must be
placed in our custody.
Thanks... to the tragedies
in Turan and Glacies...
It is clear the Exile
must be sealed away.
What does she mean by that?
Princess Lily needs
to be locked up...
If she is, it will prevent the
Exile from being used again.
Huh?
Without the Exiles, this world
will never know peace.
By nature, people are greedy...
Left unchecked...
that greed will completely
devour the world.
As has happened once already.
So there is no room
for compromise?
Surely you realized
that from the start.
Stop, both of you!
I'm begging you...
I don't want there to
be any more fighting.
Please... I ask you to
remember my mother's dream.
Vasant, I want you to stop
condemning Luscinia.
And, Luscinia...
I want you to promise you'll
never use the Exile again.
Sara's right! Listen to her...!
We all need to start
getting along...!
"Gloria, Augusta," and all that!
[applause]
Our soldiers are all
exhausted from battle...
It is time for us to set
aside our differences
for the sake of peace.
As Augusta, I hereby declare...
we have a truce!
The war is over!
Looks like the worst of
it is behind us now...
Three cheers for peace, eh?!
Hard to believe Fam's little
outburst led to this, huh?
Uh-huh--a grand ball...!
Wish I was going to it.
Why? You can't dance
to save your life!
So, are we still enemies...
or friends, again?
Things are happening
quite quickly, yes?
War has a way of severing
ties between people...
not just among friends,
but even among family.
She looks... like Raha...!
I don't see why I had
to get all dressed up.
This ball is being held
by the Augusta herself...
But I have to say,
you look pretty good.
Y'don't have to
sound so surprised!
Millia!
You should try to cheer up!
The fighting's finally over...
So that means you and
Princess Lily can make up now!
Just talk it through,
I'm sure she'll come around.
Gigi?
Enough.
Lady Fam Fan Fan.
You are largely responsible
for our newfound peace...
Would you be so kind as to honor
this old man with a dance?
Wha--Huh?!
What do you think?
The dress is lovely on you.
I was talking about the truce.
Oh, I see...
Things are still pretty
volatile, I'd say...
Serious faces
everywhere you look.
Huh...? Am I seeing
what I think I'm seeing?
Are your parents well,
Lady Fan Fan?
Uh-whoops...!
Sorry about that...
What did you ask me?
I was asking how your
mother and father are.
I dunno... I've never
seen them before.
Please forgive my rudeness.
Don't worry about it...
Most of the time I feel like
I'm part of Gigi's family.
And have you always
been a Sky Pirate?
Yeah... I've been flying for
as long as I can remember.
Your parents, too?
I'm... not sure.
I heard they were from another
country and died in an accident.
Well--
Ahh!
I am so sorry!
Well water from
the Ruins of White...
the rarest quality...
Will you join me in
drinking to our new peace?
Thank you.
I heard that you
and General Sorush
had been friends
for a long time.
It's a horrible thing, fighting
against a family member.
Or against a good friend...
I know how you feel.
I just wish I knew
how it all came to this.
Who can really say...?
Perhaps we're being tested
by a power greater than us.
Maybe we are being
put through all this
to somehow prove
that we are worthy.
I'm glad we could talk.
Princess Millia.
My name is Emma.
I've been asked to deliver this
on behalf of Major Geeth.
Major Geeth?
He wishes to speak
with you personally
about Princess Liliana.
About my sister?
I've had enough
dancing for a lifetime!
Well, you didn't do
too badly out there.
--Where's Millia?
--What?
Last Exile.
Well...? You find her?
Huh-uh... but Dad and the
others are looking for her, too.
Dang it, Millia...
Where are you?
Thank you for coming
all this way, Princess.
You wanted to speak
about my sister?
We would like to see you
on the Turan throne
instead of Princess Lily.
Are you serious?
I assure you, all the
Turan people feel this way.
What does Liliana think?
There'd be no point in
discussing it with her.
She's before me in the
line of succession...
I cannot simply disregard our
laws and crown myself queen!
That problem would be solved
if you were first in line.
As I'm sure you're well aware,
she has been branded a witch...
She's a traitor to
the Turan people...
and she controls the
Exile for Luscinia...
the man who would conquer
the world in Ades' name.
Countless people have
lost their lives.
We ask that you
fulfill your royal duty.
We will devote our lives
to protecting and
serving you, Princess.
We need you to
retake our territory
from Ades' clutches
and rebuild Turan.
You are the only
hope we have left...
Without you, Turan dies.
You want me to...
kill my own sister...?
We have disclosed this to you
with full understanding
of the consequences...
Please give us your
decision, Princess.
It is time...! Your sister
must pay for her disgrace!
It'll work... You can get near
her without raising suspicion.
It's a terrible thing to
ask of you. I know that...
but it's the only
option, Princess!
What is your answer?
You again!
I beg you, don't harm them!
How could you have
turned us over to them?
Huh?!
You're going to turn
your back on Turan, too?
What? No!
So you would betray us,
just like your sister did!
No! I didn't do this!
Lord Luscinia would like a word.
Hey!
Anything?
We're all still looking...
Someone saw her and a maid get
into a Turan military vehicle.
Military?
Princess Millia, as requested.
Welcome to the Ruins
of White, Princess...
It was from this historic place;
that the all-powerful Guild
supervised this world
so many years ago.
Where are the others?
I'm sure they'll be
suitably punished.
Why? They haven't
done anything wrong!
In the name of Turan... I demand
they be released at once!
Tell me... do you
join your countrymen
in believing Liliana
and I are cruel and evil?
That the world
and everyone in it
would be better off
if we were gone?
Come this way.
Long ago, when this world's
resources had been depleted,
the Guild proposed
an emigration.
We'd escape to the heavens...
The world would wither,
but humanity would survive.
To see this plan
become a reality,
the Guild was given
authority and resources
beyond anything
you could imagine...
Take the "Twins," for instance.
They took pairs of young boys...
To protect the Guild,
they were forced to
endure the most
brutal training...
...until they were molded
into perfect killers.
When a weapon is sharp enough,
it becomes almost impossible
not to cut yourself on it.
Liliana wishes to
see you, Princess.
Does she really?
I'm worried...
Don't be... I'm sure
she'll come back soon...
Come on, Fam...
...you know she's a whole lot
stronger than she looks.
I'm told that long ago,
crops from around the world
were brought here
for preservation.
But now...
well, just look at it...
Millia... I'm glad you
agreed to come.
Did I have much choice?
I want to know
why you betrayed Turan.
I want you to admit
what you did was wrong...
I don't understand...!
You loved our people so much.
How could you do this to them?!
You destroyed our land...
...betrayed all of us...
You've been branded the
Witch of Turan, and for what?
What are you trying
to accomplish?!
I can see I hurt you...
I never wanted
to cause you pain.
Don't avoid the question...!
Answer me!
Why are you helping Luscinia?!
All right.
If this is what you truly
believe you
must do... then do it.
Now!
Set aside your
personal feelings,
and do what must be done...
That is a princess's duty.
Please, Liliana...
By becoming a witch,
I am doing just that.
As I said... this world
is much too small for us...
If the returnee population
continues to grow...
...and deplete already
limited resources,
it will be less than a century
before we are plunged
into another age of calamity.
You still don't
have the right...
This is the only
path I can follow.
It can't be!
Luscinia's just one man...
He needs someone
else to stand by his side.
But why you?
"To rule a country, one
must make personal sacrifice
to solve unsolvable problems."
Those were our father's words.
Millia!
Hey!
Finally!
Thank goodness!
What's the matter?
Your sister's been safely
returned to the fortress.
Thank you. I appreciate
your thoughtfulness.
I want you to know
I'm truly sorry.
You're the last
person in the world
I expected to
say something like that.
Even so... we have no choice
but to continue forward.
You got to talk to her?
That's great...!
What did she say?
It's awful... I had no idea...
She's carrying such
a heavy burden...
...and she has to do
it all by herself.
Hey... look!
Usually you can only see them
if you're way further north.
Oh, wow... Just like
back in Glacies!
It's almost... frightening.
You know, I'm
actually kinda nervous.
I was getting worried
there for a while...
...but now the war is over...
...and Millia and Liliana
are speaking again...!
Holding another Grand Race isn't
just a crazy dream anymore!
Who knows, maybe
sometime next y--
What is it...? What's going on?
Why did you protect me?!
You need to live...
There is still something
you mus--must do.
Liliana!
Please Luscinia...
Look after my... sister.
Not again!
Liliana!
Wait...
Oh, no!
Millia!
Millia! What's wrong?
Can you hear me?
--Please, stay with us!
--Millia...! Millia!
Millia!
Oh, Lily! So this is why...
Lily...!
Turan Refugee Government
Special Tea Squad!
Prepare to move out!
Yes, sir!
Commence pot
and cup heat retention!
Yes, sir!
Captain! Five minutes
'til raisin scone completion!
Good... ETA to
afternoon tea.. Ten minutes...
At last... the time has
come for us to use
the power we have so
carefully cultivated!
Yes, sir!
Glory to the Turan Tea Squad!