Your Majesty...
you're still here.
Hello, Vasant.
I was just thinking
about my mother...
You knew her, didn't you?
Yes... I am proud to say so...
Augusta Farahnaz was a
truly magnificent woman.
Her ambitions were noble
and she held to them fast...
But despite the
pressures of rule,
she was rarely without a smile.
We were child soldiers then...
Your mother seemed like nothing
short of a goddess to us.
Over step.
Where'd those troublemakers
wander off to now?
Atamora!
Look at this... I got
something you need to see!
Here.
"Announcing the formation of
the Turan refugee government."
Yahoo!
Spreading this news
is a good start...
It should bring at least some
hope to the people of Turan.
It's important that they know
you're still alive and fighting.
That should at least put
a smile on their faces.
I hope so.
Right... One step closer to
the Grand Race... Let's go!
We're about halfway there.
Transport of the Sky Pirate
fleet will commence shortly.
All transport personnel,
please gather on deck.
Take a northbound detour.
The Federation still has their
First Fleet prowling about.
Roger that...! Though...
given that I'm
along for the ride,
there shouldn't
be any problems.
My regards to the
people of Anatoray.
Sure.
Impressive how many ships
they've managed to gather
in so little time.
It is... Oh, I meant to ask.
Have you heard about something
called a "Grand Race?"
Yeah...
Apparently it was a
competition that took place
long before we returned...
Why do you ask?
Curious... it's just a term I
seem to be hearing a lot lately.
Where's that...? Anatoray?
Ah... you're alone?
Yes. I'm scouting out
a new target for us.
We've still got a ways to
go before we reach fifteen.
It must be rough... Getting
dragged into this, I mean.
No... A navi's job is to
stick beside her pilot...
No matter what.
That's true, but if you
have a reckless pilot...
things get tricky.
I know.
Sometimes another part of the
job is speaking your mind...
If you always keep your
opinions to yourself,
you might both end up
losing your way.
I am pleased with how
productive this conference
of allied nations has
been, Lady Vasant.
And I am certain the Augusta
will appreciate your countries'
timely demonstration
of wisdom and prudence.
Turan were fools...
I'm sure you'll find we
exhibit far better judgment
than they ever did.
Our sincere hope is that as
members of the Ades Federation,
we can work together to
ensure prosperity for all...
Such is the true
definition of world peace.
Yes, indeed...
The Augusta is dedicated to
fulfilling her loyal subjects'
expectations for the future.
Clearly the mark
of a worthy ruler.
I think I speak for us all...
when I say it is a comfort
to have you acting
as the Federation's
representative.
Your history does make you
uniquely suited to the task.
The "Amethyst of Chaos."
To think that you,
the scion of a nation
that was once a thorn
in the Federation's side,
are now a general under the
Augusta's direct command...
Let us not speak of the past...
The Chaos region hasn't been
known as such for a long time.
The returnees' kings
have scrambled like mad
to send emissaries to this
conference of allies...
It appears they hope to
ensure their own survival...
at the expense of their
lands and their people.
I imagine they were horrified
by what happened to Turan...
I realize he was dealing
with returnees, but really,
that bodyguard of his doesn't
possess a shred of mercy.
I have to wonder how far
that bloodthirsty upstart
will need to expand the battle
lines before he's satisfied.
When you get right down to it,
he's nothing but
a glorified guard
who's got the young Augusta
wrapped around his finger.
Sadri will head from the
Corbeau Peninsula to Batos.
Kayvan will go to Reetus.
And Orang goes to Ta Opisthen...
Finally, Sorush will
head for Boreas...
They are all bountiful lands
which provide ample
resources of wheat...
Boreas in particular--
if I'm not mistaken,
they're rich in
Claudia deposits too.
That is correct, Augusta...!
You are becoming a very
knowledgeable ruler, indeed.
I have Vasant to thank for that.
There is so much to be done
if I am to become a great
Augusta like my mother.
That's the dream
closest to my heart...
I want our people to live
richer, happier lives.
You have a heart of gold...
I make this vow...
I, Sorush, will
do all in my power
to recapture our
lost territories.
Well...? Wouldn't you like
to say something, too?
I let my achievements
speak for me,
rather than resort to
long-winded bravado.
Be careful, so that
you may return safely...
And, Sorush, try not
to get too friendly
with any girls you
encounter along the way.
Why did she say that, Orang?
What have you been
telling the Augusta?
Luscinia!
The pieces have come together.
Preparations are in place
to conquer each nation.
Then we shall begin
tonight, as planned.
Also, I came across this
in former Turan territory.
A Turan refugee government?
So, she has made
her first move...
Well... It seems
Princess Millia...
is doomed to lose
everything yet again.
What?!
All my precious
ships?! Gone?!
"We've moved all the ships
you've acquired so far...
They've been relocated
to a safe location,
pending completion
of your mission."
"You have seven battleships
to go... Best of luck."
Where is this "safe location"?
Who knows?
My goodness...
this is quite a place.
Yep... Eldorado
entertainment area...
They hold lots of underground
Vanship races here...
That's what it's most known for.
As you can see, we have a
referral from Duke Bollner.
All right, boys...!
Time to make some money...!
Today's gonna rule!
We're gonna make a man
outta you yet, little guy.
Just you wait. Ha!
Excuse me, I take it
you're Lady Roshanak Babar,
the Federation baroness.
And you would be...?
Fam Fan Fan...
I'm a Vanship pilot.
Is that so...?
And what does a Vanship pilot
such as yourself want with me?
We were told you're a regular
patron of Eldorado,
and that you're particularly
interested in the Vanship races
that are held here.
Indeed...
In fact, I have my own
participant racing today.
I have an offer...
I'll compete against
this contestant of yours.
If I win, I want ownership
of your state battleship,
the Nahid.
Very well... and in exchange,
if my man wins...
My compensation will
be... that cutie.
Huh?!
What can I say?
My weakness for young boys
is almost as strong as
my love of gambling...
And this one here
is very much my type.
You're gonna make another
one of these bets, milady?
Oh, Lady Roshanak...
you certainly do have
a fondness for them.
Awesome... We got this.
Fam, shush!
That's why I'm dressed
this way? To act as bait?!
Don't worry about it...
The races they hold here're
always real low-level stuff...
Right?
Yeah... I guess...
Yashbal!
Yes, Mistress...
How may I serve you?
The Yashbal Anand?! No way!
What the heck is he doing here?
Um, who?
He... he's a pilot.
One of the ones who
flew in the Grand Race!
My, aren't you well-informed...?
Especially for one so young...
Yashbal was indeed a
finalist in the Grand Race.
He has quite the reputation.
Even here, where he's known
only as the Unbeatable Falcon.
Hey...! No fair,
usin' a fake name!
By the way, after a
hundred-twenty races,
he's undefeated.
If you lose,
I'll kill you myself.
Last Exile.
It's set up as a
twenty-lap speed race...
The course is ten miles long...
Which means it'll last
around two hours, I guess.
We need a strategy...
That final deceleration
point will be the key...
And it's safe to
assume our opponent
knows the course inside and out.
Goin' up against a Grand
Race finalist though...
Beating this guy's not
gonna be a piece o'cake.
Yeah, unfortunately,
I think that's a bit
of an understatement.
Especially if he's stayed
active in competitions
since the Grand Race...
unlike Dad and the
other Sky Pirates.
On the bright side...
we've still got another
Grand Race to hold.
Aw yeah...! They're about
to start, you guys!
Remember, make our move
on the final lap...
Until then, we can take things a
bit slower and even fall behind
a little where
everything bottlenecks...
Just don't lose him!
Roger that... I'll leave it to
you as far as the timing goes.
Go, Fam.
Amazing... this guy's
a serious racer.
Man, look at him go...!
He's got a huge lead!
He... looks like
he's gonna crash.
Dude's got guts, and he
ain't afraid to show it.
No wonder he's the
favorite to win...
No one else's even comin' close!
Worried?
No... Fam won't lose
to him. I'm sure of it.
Let's chat a bit...
Have you... heard about
this new Turan government?
Wherever you go, it's all
anyone's talking about...
I can't believe they're still
determined to resist...
Not after how thoroughly the
Federation defeated them.
I don't know about that kinda
stuff... I'm just a kid.
Everyone's saying
how ridiculous it is.
You should be ashamed...
As a group, you have been
motivated only by greed and
the selfish desire to
protect your own interests...
Even more despicably,
you are guilty of countless
crimes against the state.
We have received
reliable reports...
that you have willingly turned
over your personal battleships
to Princess Millia of Turan...
and assisted in her uprising...
Today it was announced
that Turan has established
a refugee government...
This was only possible because
of your traitorous assistance.
No...! That's absurd...!
We would never even consider
giving aid to Turan.
You must understand, our
battleships were stolen,
that was all the
Sky Pirates' doing...
We didn't willingly offer
them up for their use!
These accusations are ludicrous!
This is a royal decree...
You are hereby
sentenced to death.
It's... the Extermination Squad!
He barely slowed down at all!
Fam!
This brings back memories...
It's almost like the
Grand Race itself.
Of course... it's no more
than a false veneer.
These ladies...? Once royalty
in powerful kingdoms...
In exchange for
the small sacrifice
of their homelands and pride...
they were made
members of the nobility.
The same bargain I made.
Just forsake your kingdom...
and you'll save yourself, right?
Patriotism, responsibility...
Do they honestly matter...?
Fighting might save your
precious pride... But why...?
Such tenacity is noble,
but it will simply lead to
more conflict and bloodshed.
It's pointless.
I couldn't disagree
with you more.
To live a life
devoid of honor...
utterly empty of any meaning...
I would prefer death.
Nothing is going
to save you now...
Please don't make this any
harder than it needs to be.
We will kill each
and every person
who dares sully the
name of the Augusta!
I can't keep up.
It's down to the final lap...
He's got this in the bag!
Come on, Fam.
You gotta get it in gear!
Don't let it end like this!
Gigi, how much
farther to the goal?
We've only got a
quarter-mile to go.
Right...! Cut the fuel!
Gigi!
All right. I'm on it!
Please, Fam.
Here goes. Jettisoning
left wired spear.
Dumping all fuel, coolant,
and Claudia reserves...
That should do it!
What? She dumped their fuel?
Huh...? Huh?!
She jettisoned it to
drop the extra weight.
That's one gutsy
last-ditch gamble...!
Even so... How's she
gonna make the turn?
I won't lose!
Oh, no...! They're gonna crash!
Now!
Wow...! She actually
pulled it off!
Yeah, they won!
Aw, man...! I lost it all!
That was amazing! You won!
Thanks, Millia!
Great job... but please...
don't ever scare me
like that again!
I don't think I could take it!
Yeah sure... but...
at least we put on
a good show, right?
Yes, just incredible...!
My heart was beating so fast...
It was nearly as intense
as an actual Grand Race.
You were nothing more
than a common bodyguard.
How can you do this...?
Have you forgotten
Lady Farahnaz's wish?
I have not forgotten the
former Augusta's wish.
But granting it...
Requires your blood.
The purge has begun...
Purify the world in
the name of the Augusta.
We'll make the
announcement at dawn.
Understood.
I never imagined they
would use that strategy
to negotiate the turn.
I have failed you
shamefully, Mistress...
I accept any punishment
you choose to give me.
Somehow, I think this
may be--for the best.
She won the Nahid...
It's hers to take.
Unbelievable...!
You mean to say none of
you put money on me?!
Well, I hope you've all
learned your lesson...
From now on, there
better be no question
who you're dealin' with!
I am the future champion
of the Grand Race, got it?!
What's the matter, Teddy?
Um.. during that last race,
Ignace and the others kinda
talked me into, well...
They talked you
into placing a bet?
Right.. So, of course,
I bet on you and Fam.
Huh?
Then the crowd went
wild about some upset,
but I don't really know
what that means...
Am I supposed to do
something with this ticket?
You haven't cashed it in?
"Cashed it in"?
What's that mean?
Somebody, quick!
Stop the ship!
We need to go back to
Eldorado right now!