A soldier is a sword...
and is used at its
wielder's discretion...
Our duty is a simple one...
We need only be mighty swords.
The one who wields
us is determined...
She will do anything
to achieve her goal...
She will stop at nothing...
even should her swords become
bloodstained and
broken in the process.
And that... is what worries
me more than anything else.
Connected Passed Pawn.
♪ Hey there...! It's your
birthday...! Get happy! ♪
Happy birthday, Fam!
Fam, hello!
That's strange.
I can't believe it.
You're really leaving?
Well, we've captured
fifteen Federation ships...
just like we promised.
Yeah, I know... still...
Don't worry...
I'll tell everyone in Kartoffel
why you're staying behind.
They'll understand.
This isn't right... Gigi...
I can't fly without you!
Why not ask Princess Millia?
She's very knowledgeable...
and at least she
has good judgment...
Something I'm missing.
I'm sorry... I'm just not...
fit to be your navi anymore.
I'm sure you and the
Princess'll be great together.
You're the best navi there is!
No, I'm not... I'm nothing.
Don't say that, Gigi!
You don't know anything, Fam!
I heard what happened...
Talk about a bad
first impression.
Encountering Glacies wasn't
exactly part of the plan.
We violated their airspace...
then fought inside
their territory...
We must seem like
total savages to them.
Conflict will be unavoidable.
Seems that way...
I doubt even offering the
Silvius as a gift would help.
Where's Vincent?
On his way now...
Can't wait to see his reaction.
He's in for a shock,
seeing the invincible
Silvius all beat up like this.
Do you know what would've helped
us avoid taking so much damage?
Having our Vanship squadron's
captain around for the fight.
It really would've helped
if you'd shown up sooner.
I know.
Is Millia here?
I burnt it! I'm sorry!
Hush!
Why are you trying to avoid Fam?
I'm too ashamed to face her.
But it weren't your
fault, Princess.
Tell me... what am I supposed
to do at a time like this?
I wish my sister was here...
She would have known
exactly how to handle it.
Soup's gettin' cold.
Delicious...
Verify system check!
Everything looks groovy!
"Groovy?" Really?
Yahoo!
Come on, Dio, cut it out!
We're not here to play games!
We're supposed to be
heading to the border!
I know that!
Oh, you do? Coulda fooled me...!
Fam, say something!
Hello...? Fam!
Impressive.
But they shouldn't bother us
as long as we stay
outside the border.
I'm not so sure...
They could come back
with reinforcements.
Let's get this done
quick, just in case.
A tweak here and there and
she'll be flying again...
A tough ship to bring
down... Good job.
Fam seems kind of upset, huh?
Well, fighting's a part
of life on the Silvius...
It's not like we're
making them stay...
If they don't like it, they
can leave anytime they want.
They're not officially part
of the crew or anything.
You gonna call it in?
Oh... yeah.
Recirculation valve repaired.
Roger that... Start the engine.
Starting engine!
Output increasing...!
Ten... Twenty...
forty percent, and...
Liftoff!
She's returning to Kartoffel?
Mm-hm...
What about you?
I never stopped being part
of the Silvius' crew...
I had a lot of fun
flying with you guys.
But my playtime is over now.
I see... Gigi is
set on going back.
We head out at fifteen
hundred hours...
We'll be going that
way for supplies,
so we can drop you off.
Thank you for
everything, ma'am...
I really appreciate it.
Giselle... Do you remember
the advice I gave you before?
That sometimes, in
order to do your job,
you have to say
what's on your mind.
I've been taking
Gigi for granted.
She's always been
there for me...
so I assumed she
always would be...
I never stopped to think about
what she might be feeling.
I've been there, too.
I had someone in my life who
was very important to me...
I took for granted he
would always be there.
I just assumed he felt
the same way I did.
I never actually asked
him about his feelings...
nor did I ever tell
him about mine.
Now he's gone,
and I'll never know.
Oh no! Careful, Princess!
Fire! It's on fire!
Let me!
Thanks, Gigi.
Sure.
Potato... pancakes?
Well... yes...
They're for Fam...
They're her favorite,
aren't they?
Sometimes having a tasty
meal cheers people up...
I thought you two could
eat them together.
I'm so sorry...
This was my issue...
Turan versus Ades...
I should never've
dragged you into it...
It's caused you and
Fam so much trouble.
I feel terrible!
Please forgive me!
No... Millia!
You have nothing
to be sorry for...
Really... That's just
the way Fam is.
She couldn't ignore--
You could've just taken
her away from there!
Let me be your wings.
If we've met our quota, we won't
need to stay on the Silvius.
We can go back
to Kartoffel, Fam.
I'm sorry...
I'm just not... fit to
be your navi anymore.
I'm sure you'll and the
Princess'll be great together.
She couldn't ignore you
when you needed help.
She's just not built for it.
What's the matter?
I've been so awful...
I was only thinking
about myself...
and I said such terrible things.
The look on her face...
I never meant to hurt her...
--I want to--
I want to make it
up to her somehow.
I know, me too!
I can't stand to see her
feeling that way, either.
It's settled then.
We'll do it together.
Right.
So let's think about this...
What can we do to cheer her up?
Duh...! Today's Fam's birthday!
It is? Really?
I can't believe I
forgot! I'm a jerk.
Although... The day
isn't over yet, you know.
Right!
Last Exile.
You guys!
Man, where is everyone?
Dio?
That's a tall order.
All righty... first thing...
Yeah, they jumped ship.
Could you not have
phrased that differently?
It's the truth.
The best ones are
nice and round--
still fresh
around the stem.
Smells wonderful!
A gallon of milk and all of your
oranges and potatoes, please.
--A goat!
--So cute!
Gigi...! Let's go!
'Kay, I'm coming!
'Bout ready to go?
Yes.
Enough slackin' off for ya.
Hey, cool... Check out
the mast-topper... Huh?
Hey, Fam...! Pass!
Come on, I'm open!
Elio!
Get it!
Go long!
Let's see if we
can even the score.
Hey! Hockey game up on deck!
What's going on...? Well, men?
One... helluva game...
Fam's got a real knack
for--Oh...! Captain!
Close but not quite!
Jus' warmin' up!
Come on! Let's do it!
Yeah!
Fam Fan Fan?
I wish I had a cooler name...
Fritz and those guys say it
sounds like a pet's name.
Nobody else has a name
like that, it's neat.
You think so?
Fam, please put it down!
You're gonna get in trouble!
It's a long way down,
birdbrain, better be careful!
Nuh-uh!
It's Daddy!
Hi, Atamora!
It's always been the two of us.
Just like sisters.
Soaring through the sky...
Melting into the wind...
That's my dream.
That's our dream.
Fam!
Sorry!
Gigi!
Fam... I wanted to say...
You came back.
'Course I did.
Would you like to
play, Princess?
Oh... you want me?
Hey, Fam... we got
another teammate!
Huh?
Millia!
They got six players now.
Guys, we could use some
extra hands over here.
No problem.
We've got you covered.
I thought I'd lost
everything that mattered.
I had to help her...
Nobody should be alone.
For as long as I can remember,
I've always wanted
to support her.
We'll always be there
for each other...
No matter what happens.
Think you can get past me?!
Millia! Heads up!
You might want to stand back.
The Princess...?!
What am I supposed to do?
Do I stop her? She's royalty!
--Gigi!
--Got it!
Yeah!
Together with Gigi...
To help Millia!
Together with Fam...
We'll see another
Grand Race someday!
Ready!
♪ Hey, there it's your
birthday! Get happy! ♪
♪ Happy when you're born! Happy
when you're old and gray! ♪
♪ So congrats...!
Here's to you...! ♪
♪ Happy birthday...
from everyone to Fam! ♪
Make a wish... Fam.
Everybody eat up
before it gets cold!
A toast to Miss Fam Fan Fan...!
--Cheers!
--Thank you!
Sorry. It was supposed
to be a secret.
We were hopin' to surprise
you... and it worked!
Here you are.
Congratulations...
You got all fifteen ships.
Well done, Fam.
Are you really gonna leave now?
Our Skyfish hunt isn't over yet.
I turned sixteen today.
We still need to take down
Ades and reclaim Turan.
So I'm not going anywhere.
Here... my birthday
present to you.
All right! Now you're officially
part of the Silvius crew.
Hmm... sounds lively.
A welcome party?
You shouldn't have.
Vincent!
Hello, Tatiana... Great work.
You are...?
Yes, forgive me...
Commander-in-Chief
of the United Kingdom
of Anatoray-Disith's
Vanguard Unit.
My name is Vincent Alzey.
And you're Princess Millia...
royal deputy of the Turan
refugee government...
A pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
You guys! Thank you
so much for today!
So, Fam... now that
you're sixteen...
is there anybody that
you're interested in?
Interested in?
Is there?
I haven't really thought
about it... Hmm...
Oh! There is someone!
Oh! Really? Who is it?
That old Ades admiral.
He's interesting!
Oh... I see...
That's not exactly what
I meant, but okay...