We got company...! Open fire!
Protect the Urbanus!
Hi...! Sorry for the wait.
Dio!
The Federation sent assassins.
We need to leave Anatoray.
No more games.
Block.
Who're you?
Where are Gigi and Millia?
I--There were two girls with me.
Have you seen them?
We're about a hundred
eighteen miles...
north-northeast of
Kurbis lookout.
We're really far north.
Yeah... and you know
what that means...
Gigi...! Millia!
You guys are okay...!
I was so worried about you!
We're fine, see for yourself.
And you...? Are you okay, too?
Yep...!
Who's that girl? She doesn't
understand anything I say.
And where the heck are we?
Gigi figured it out.
We're in Glacies.
We crash-landed
inside their border.
Well, we survived...
Good job, girl.
I still can't believe we managed
to escape that firefight.
I thought for sure we
were gonna die out there.
Did that Glacien girl rescue us?
Most likely.
Wonder about the Silvius...
I sure hope they
got out all right.
Do you think she can be fixed?
She's taken pretty
heavy damage, though...
We don't have all the
parts to make repairs.
So what do we do now?
Why's someone from
Glacies helping us?
I wonder who she is, anyway.
Someone important?
Yeah...? But how do we
know we can trust her...?
She could be
holding us prisoner!
If that was actually the case,
don't you think she would've
stripped us of everything
we have by now?
That's a good point...
She hasn't even
taken our tools away.
But this is Glacies
we're talking about...
Maybe she's just
waiting to eat us!
That's ridiculous.
She's saying "Please, kindred
spirit... grant me life."
Wait, you speak--?
Of course.
Now she's saying... "Forget
nothing... soul of mine."
"Give praise to the world...
and be thankful of it all."
Oh, wow...! It smells so good!
Mm, it does!
Millia.
Millia il Velch
Cutrettola Turan?
Impressive!
She knows your full name!
I still can't remember it all!
Manners.
Oh...! Sorry!
"We are the Winged Priestesses.
We protect our motherland...
You and your friend
came to our aid once."
Oh...! Right, that!
"Why did you save my pilots?"
"May the wind guide and carry
wings that become lost."
She says, "You're too nice."
Well, so are you!
She said...
It's okay. I think we
got the point of that.
Viola!
As we speak, the fleets
are assembling
one hundred-fifty
miles northeast
of the Boreas Fortress.
Kayvan, Orang, and Sorush...
you will command your fleets
in a joint operation.
And together, crush Glacies.
Gloria, Augusta!
Who do you intend
to form the vanguard?
Batos... Rhaetus...
Ta Opisthen... And Chaos.
We're sending the
provincial fleets, Premier?
The Augusta adores
the provinces...
I hope we can count
on their assistance
to safeguard her future
and that of her subjects.
Yes! Even should it
cost me my life.
I will do my utmost
to serve Her Majesty.
As will I. Gloria, Augusta!
Gloria, Augusta!
Thank you, men...
Together we shall
achieve our goal...
With your help we will
reclaim our rightful lands.
We could've received
no greater honor.
Yes... This shows how much
the Augusta trusts us.
We will be proud to
lead the vanguard...
The Survivors of Chaos
will fight valiantly.
Thank you... All of you.
The Glacies offensive
will begin in three days.
I will fulfill my duty...
and nothing more.
I have not forgiven
you, Luscinia.
I know, Princess.
That book. Is it
from the Silvius?
It is... The captain
gave it to me...
It's a ship operations manual.
They're okay, right...?
Teddy and the others...
We will see them
again, won't we?
Of course we will...
They'll be fine...
No one can take
down the Silvius.
The captain promised they'd
come get us, remember...?
No need to worry.
What's she saying?
She says we can use
these for repairs,
and she won't tell
her superiors...
but as soon as we're--Fam!
Hold on! Wait up!
Hey...! Thank you!
Umm... Let's see...
er... thank you...
You understand?
How else can I say it?
I want to thank you!
Ah, come on! Thanks a lot!
Whatever we need...
she says she'll get for us.
For real?! That's incredible!
You met Millia... but the
quiet one there is Gigi.
Oh... and my name's Fam.
Uh... F-Fam...?
Yep!
Hard to believe
we've come this far.
At last.
Our time is at hand.
Last Exile.
Thanks!
Oh, great! Do you think you
could get these things next?
If it's no trouble.
Fam! You didn't
eat your carrots!
Fresh vegetables are
hard to find out here...
It's rude to let
'em go to waste...
Open. "Ah!"
I'll only eat 'em if
they're cooked first.
Eat!
Later, okay?
Now!
Dyan.
Giselle, Dyan is
asking where the--
I'm not sure I'm
understanding this right...
Do you know what
a "windshield" is?
Just what it sounds like, a
piece of glass for protection.
If we had one of those,
I wouldn't be able to feel
the wind on my face.
Hey! What was that big sigh for?
What the heck do you
have against the wind?
She's asking where
the ship's weapons are.
Aren't any!
There...! I'm all
done up here, Fam.
I'm finished here, too...
Why should we have weapons?
You don't need 'em to fly.
That's freezing!
Stop...! Leave it alone, Fam!
Well, if you won't take
it off someone's gotta!
I would if you'd
stop staring at me!
Let me help you with that.
That's it, Gigi, pull!
That was amazing, Dyan!
It's like they worship you!
"The sky is a battlefield."
"Flying on ships
without weapons...?
Saving others for nothing?"
"I don't get it...
I don't understand
why you fly this way."
"What reason is there?"
Why do we fly...?
Well, because we
want to, of course!
Flying's so much fun...!
Zooming around,
doing big loops,
taking steep dives,
racing people!
"That's what you
consider fun?" she asks.
That's it!
You're going to be in
the new Grand Race, too...!
Maybe then you'll get it.
Ah...!
It's when Vanships from all over
the world come together to fly!
And everyone's happy!
On the day of the Grand Race
there's no fighting or violence.
Just people coming
together in peace.
Not like now, where it's
war wherever you go...
I don't like it...
The sky's so full of hate...
It has to stop...
And that's why...
I'm not gonna rest until we
have another Grand Race...!
Then everyone can smile again!
She says, "That's rubbish."
"An ominous sign."
"There was an aurora
that night, as well."
Aurora?
"The night before
the... Grand Race."
"That's when we decided
we would never again
trust anyone from
outside our own land."
"Or else even more
blood would be shed."
No way! We won't let it
end like that again!
I agree.
Heh...! And you'll be
right there with us, Dyan.
Fam!
The Grand Race...! In or out?!
Fam, stop!
Well? Come on! In or out...?
Hey! Just calm down, would ya?
Now you're in for it!
Take it easy! I'm just
tryin' to help, Fam!
No, wait!
Dyan...! Challenge!
And here's the deal,
if I beat you...
You're in the Grand Race!
What?! She isn't coming up?!
Fam?
--Fam?!
Fuel, coolant, Claudia...
All good to go...
Altimeter, gyro tuning,
and controls are green.
We're all clear on
preflight checks.
Roger that... Starting!
Wanna try it?
Throttle control is
in the headset...
Just remember, you wanna go full
throttle when you start her up.
Think of it like this...
If you look downward
to move forward,
the rest'll come naturally!
You've flown tons
of times before...
It's the same as that.
Give it some gas.
The throttle...!
Give it full throttle!
Dyan!
That was a waste of fuel.
Take a look at that!
Dyan!
Thank you again
for all your help!
What was that?
Some kind of goodbye?
She says she doesn't think
we'll ever see each other again.
Aww... what'd she
go and say that for?
Well... there was
one other thing.
She hopes we can soar
through the same sky someday.
Luscinia's going to
be here before long.
As soon as we get
out of Glacies,
we'll track down the Silvius
again... and once we do...
We're gonna go
save Princess Lily!
Multiple fleets at ten o'clock!
That many?!
Those aren't their main fleets.
They're not Federation ships?
They are flying Federation
flags, but it's not Luscinia...
Looks like...
Rhaetus... Ta Opisthen...
Chaos?!
Those are the
Federation's main fleets!
Why would they have brought the
Provincial Fleets with them?
Now what?
What's going on?
Those are decoys.
We have to tell
Dyan immediately!
Wow, you speak the Glacies
language perfectly, Millia!
Of course.. I am royalty..
Okay then, tell me
how you say, "I win."
Uh... "Ya pobedila."
Now how about...
"Try and beat me, if you dare!
You'll never win in
a million years!"
I'm sensing a theme, here...
Why do you want to learn how
to say stuff like that, Fam?
Why do you think?