The White Legacy...
Weak square.
Keep moving, vermin.
You are enemies of the people.
These traitors forsook their
homelands for personal gain...
Their selfish actions have
hindered our sacred crusade.
Who knows how many fields
could've been planted
with the money these
so-called leaders
greedily leached from
their own people?
However, they have
been stopped...
and punished in a manner
befitting their crimes.
And now, no one can
deny our resolve.
We have shown it for all to see.
A clear path lies before us.
All of this world's fertile
lands shall be ours once again.
Our forces continue
to push forward,
beyond the northern reaches
of the sacred Grand Lake.
Soon they shall reach your
former homeland of Glacies...
and the returnees who
have stolen it from you.
My people! Let us retake
our land together!
Gloria... Augusta!
That was a magnificent
address...
You must be exhausted...
Perhaps you should
get some rest.
They're all dead...
all of those people...
and it's because... of me!
You mustn't say that.
I am so young... and weak...
That's what killed them.
So many.
That's not true, Your Majesty.
Please believe me
when I tell you that
none of this
is your fault...
They were undone
by their own greed!
I'm supposed to protect
the people, it's my duty...!
A good ruler doesn't harm her
subjects, she earns their trust.
Like my mother!
I'm so sorry... I'm so sorry.
Your Majesty,
I'm here for you...
Do not ever forget that...
I will always see
your will be done.
We've stamped out most of
the resistance movements...
We've also begun collecting
capital in territories
owned by the surrendered nobles.
Good work... We owe this
success to your swift action...
The Almighty Spear of
Ades triumphs again.
You are too kind, Premier.
We shall not be attacked
from behind, now...
Our obstacles are melting
away... soon the last will fall.
And finally we'll be
able to move forward.
The Grand Lake's
southern coast will be
under our complete
control before long...
The next step will be taking
the battle northward...
and beginning full-scale efforts
to reclaim the Lake's
northern coast.
Kumari, Arshia,
and Sepehr, yes...
all three should yield
quickly enough...
They are small nations.
Vasant's negotiations
were effective...
I doubt anyone will offer
much resistance... except...
Except Glacies.
We can safely assume
the Federation will now
turn its attention
north of the Grand Lake.
When that happens, they'll
come to blows with Glacies...
They'll have to.
Will it be a head-on
confrontation?
Most likely.
Glacies has remained
totally independent
since the moment
it was founded...
I'm sure they don't even notice
when the Federation usurps
other territories...
But I expect it will be a
completely different story
when it's their land
being threatened.
In many ways, they're even more
trouble than the Federation.
They refuse any and all
negotiations and attack
the moment somebody
crosses over their border...
They don't put much
stock in the idea
that your enemy's enemy
can be your friend.
Which means our future
is going to be determined
by whatever action
Glacies chooses to take.
I suppose all we can do for now
is trust in Vincent's
ability to bargain.
Perhaps we should do
some preliminary recon.
Lay in a new course...
Head for the Glacies border.
How's the tea? Teddy taught me.
Listen up, lad.
Germs and vermin
are always lookin'
to infiltrate
your territory...
You gotta keep a sharp eye.
Aye-aye, sir!
But I'm telling you, this is
the perfect chance for us!
Don't talk with your
mouth full... It's rude.
These purges they've
started carrying out
are gonna make the
Federation even stronger...
Come on... This is
a huge opportunity...!
We need to take advantage
of it while we can.
You see, as the nobles
are being purged,
the battleships belonging
to their territories
are being captured and taken
back to the Ades Federation...
That's the most
notable extraction.
That fleet is being transported
from the northern
land of Fields...
It consists of eight
brand-new ships,
constructed
only six months ago.
Eight ships...?
But the agreement only
calls for one more.
True... But Fam thinks...
I think we should go
all-out for this last run...
Imagine the look on the
Captain's face if we succeed...
She'll never be expecting
eight ships at once!
That would be quite
a sight to behold.
Oh, no. Not you too?
All right, that settles it...
We're gonna show Captain
Tatiana what we're made of!
Thank you for the book.
Oh... finished with it already?
Yes.
All of it...?
Even including "A Summary
of Signal Lights and Flares
per the Trans-Grand
Lake Treaty?"
Yes... I found it
most informative.
It sounds like you won't be
needing my guidance anymore...
It's all yours...
Delve into whatever
subjects pique your interest.
So, um... Now that
I've done the research,
I hoped you would tell
me the best strategy
for destroying an entire
Ahdes fleet single-handedly.
I meant it when I told you
there was no such thing...
Fighting boils
down to resources:
yours and your enemy's.
Giselle.
Gathering information
for your mission?
Yeah... there are still some
things I'm uneasy about.
That's very sensible...
Fam could learn a thing
or two from you.
Not really...
Fam's fine the way she is...
Background research is
just part of the job...
It's my duty as her navi.
We can't afford to
fail this operation...
Ades is gonna keep getting
stronger and stronger...
Hunting Skyfish won't
be so easy anymore...
Not like it was.
Please, Giselle...
I just need your help
for a bit longer...
I'll put Fam's fleet
to good use, I swear...
With it, I will reclaim Turan.
I will make your dream real.
There will be a new Race.
A flock of Grand Birds...!
What's that? You wanna race?
All right, you're on...!
Let the second Grand Race
qualifiers begin!
So, Fam...
Yeah?
At the end of today, we'll have
the fifteen ships we agreed to.
Have you thought about
what we'll do next?
Next, huh...?
If we've met our quota, we won't
need to stay on the Silvius...
We can go back to Kartoffel.
I'm worried about
Adele and René.
Félicité isn't old
enough to help Mom
with the younger ones so much...
and you know my dad...
He's practically helpless
when he's not in the sky...
I mean... don't you miss
Fritz and the others, too?
Yeah...! Don't you miss us?
Hey, ladies!
Fritz! Heine! Johann?!
Whadaya know, you are alive!
So Birdbrain escaped the
infamous Silvius, huh...?
I didn't see that one coming.
Atamora's pretty
ticked, by the way.
It's Dad.
You can rest easy, sir...
Looks like they're
safe and sound.
Yeah, so... are you guys
here to bring us back?
Is that what you think...?
Sorry... We came for the
Skyfish headin' this way.
The ships Ades is transporting?!
So, you're after
them, too, huh...?
I hope you're ready
for a tough battle!
That's Zwiebel... Pilze...
Karotten... and Kürbis...
...even Spargel!
They're all here!
Oh, no! Here they come!
No...! Those ships are
our prey, not yours!
You're wrong about
that, Birdbrain!
Good tailwinds, you guys!
Hey, Fam! Keep an eye out
for currents blowing
into the canyon.
Roger that!
Skyfish! And they're
all gonna be mine!
We're in the best position.
Great job, Gigi!
First harpoon's
got my name on it!
It's the Jagannath!
What's the Third
Fleet doing here?!
Sky Pirate docks and multiple
small vessels ahead...
Distance, two thousand.
It's about time.
Last Exile.
This is the Ades
Federation fleet...
The time has come for
you to pay the price
for your unrelenting defiance
and multiple acts
of depredation.
Prepare for
counter-air combat...
We shall obliterate
all who stand in the way
of the Augusta's
noble cause.
Sir!
Gloria... Augusta!
Activating rapid-fire system...
Actuating coupled anti-aircraft
guns numbers one and two.
I should've seen
this coming... Sorry.
Look out!
Ades caught us in their trap!
We can't go up!
There's nowhere to run!
Damn it!
This was all just a set up...
We took the Federation's
bait, all right.
Well, what now?!
How're we supposed to
get outta here, Gigi?
Give me a second to think.
What are we up against...?
I only see Third
Fleet's Jagannath
and Field Squadrons
one through four.
This isn't their
entire main force...
These're all long distance
ships-of-the-line.
They use 'em for decisive
fleet-against-fleet battles...
which means...
The lower turrets on these ships
can't match the Vespa's speed...
We need to slip beneath the
fleet and skim along the water
to get through the canyon.
Gotcha!
Lower anti-aircraft guns...
prepare to open fire.
Lower guns,
prepare to open fire!
Guns below, too?
They're only Sky Pirates.
They don't have the
speed or maneuverability
of Glacies rocket fighters...
They aren't likely to present
enough of a challenge for us
to gain useful intel
for the new weapon.
Quiet, Crèche...
There's no such thing as
a meaningless mission.
Sorry, sir... I'm out of line.
Gigi!
Purge the repair deck,
on the double!
Atamora!
No...! They're hit!
Daddy...! You can't sink!
--No!
--Calm down Gigi, it's fine!
Only the repair
deck's been hit...
That's not enough
to take 'em down.
But...!
Atamora would never
fall so easily...
You should know that
better than anyone.
Think...! There's gotta
be something we can do.
Look at the Grand Birds...
That's it!
Fam! The wind is
too strong up there!
Don't worry...!
The Grand Birds have just
shown us the way out of this!
The current changes...
Don't you see...?
It shifts for just a moment
when the glaciers hit the water!
No, it's impossible!
The Grand Birds made it,
didn't they...?
It's all timing...
There has to be one moment
when we can slip through.
We just gotta find it.
By the time they fly off,
it'll be too late...
We would need a shockwave to
change the current ourselves.
I know!
Those are Fam's signal flares.
She wants us to
draw their fire?!
Yep, that sounds like
Birdbrain, all right.
She does realize they've been
blasting at us the whole time?
Signal from Fam's ship!
"We're heading into the
canyon... Follow my lead!
Be sure to attract the
Third Fleet's fire."
Men! Follow Fam's lead!
Good tailwinds!
Those girls'll be
the death o' me...
Sir...!
The Sky Pirates appear to be
withdrawing into the canyon!
Intel collection for
the new weapon is
approaching completion, sir.
Very good. I'd say it's high
time we finish them off.
Fire main guns!
Move, now!
A gustnado is forming!
Engines to maximum!
Use auxiliary circuits!
What are you fools doing...?
Get after the Sky Pirates, now!
But... we can't, sir.
It's impossible to
get a fix on them
in the middle of all
those Grand Birds.
Milady!
I trust you're all
holding up well?
We are, my lady...
We surviving citizens of Chaos
are too strong to
be brought low.
Your pardon... but, we...
well, we were wondering about
this recent purging
of the returnees.
Quiet, fool...
Don't put her on the spot!
We're not here to ambush
her with such questions.
Right, I'm sorry, my lady.
I understand why you
would be uneasy...
There is no need to worry,
all will be well...
And I can assure you,
the Augusta knows
the people of Chaos are
loyal to her and her reign.
Of course she does...!
What was I thinking?
See, I told ya you
were being foolish.
You feel better now?
Yeah, world's
biggest scaredy-cat!
Sure did a number on us.
Yeah.
So what happens now...?
What do we do?
What are you talking about...?
Same as we've always done...
Hunt Skyfish and survive.
Yeah... maybe...
but it's gettin' ugly.
Time to go.
All that for nothin'.
What a waste.
Come on... we should leave, too.
Not yet, Gigi...
Type something up for me.
You sure about this...?
Letting 'em go?
A Sky Pirate has honor...
We keep the promises we make.
"I'm sorry, Atamora.
We can't come home quite yet.
I know I'm being selfish...
but please...
just give me a little longer...
Millia still needs us."
Come on, why so glum...?
We just have to find new
prey to go after, that's all.
We made it out of the
canyon, didn't we...?
And that was totally
thanks to you.
Nothing's gonna stop us...
long as we're together.
Sure.
Approaching Vespa...
It's Fam, Captain.
Fam's ship has returned...
Open hangar hatch.
I'm going to go and meet them.
Right... See you soon, Princess.
Multiple engines heard...
They're behind Fam...
Distance, Oh-Five.
They followed us back!
The Anshar?!
Why didn't we detect
those ships sooner?
Receiving a communication
from Admiral Sadri,
Commandant of the First Fleet.
What's the bastard say?
"Hand over Princess Millia..."
"...immediately..."
"Refuse and...
we sink your ship."
Teddy?
Yes, Princess?
Isn't this the
maintenance storeroom?
No, I've annexed it!
As of today, it's the office
of the Turan Refugee Government
and your own private study!
Considering how much
Ignace likes to gamble,
you'd think he'd
be better at it.
Teddy, you didn't...
At this rate, it won't be
long before I've expanded
our territory to include
the whole of the Silvius!
Just you wait and see, Princess!
I'm not sure I want to.