Cheers to Fam's tears!
Cheers!
Congratulations. You successfully
captured fifteen battleships.
Our Skyfish hunt isn't over yet.
I turned 16 today.
We still have to beat up the
Federation and take back Turan!
I'm staying right here!
Dear Mom and Dad. How are you?
Have René, Félicité, and Adele
been behaving themselves?
We're currently on the Silvius.
It's crazy to think that we're hunting
Skyfish aboard the infamous Reaper.
Skyfish hunting used to be part of
my job as a Sky Pirate, after all.
The first harpoon is mine!
Go!
"Hey, you creepy pervert of a captain..."
Creepy pervert?!
"I'm gonna make sure every port in the world
hears about how much of a chicken you are..."
"Hope you enjoy it!"
--Wow, that's harsh, Gisey!
--But it was your idea, Fam...
Shoot down that Vespa!
Breach!
We've caught ourselves a Skyfish!
The world has always been
filled with territorial conflict,
but we Sky Pirates have remained
neutral and independent through it all,
soaring freely through the skies.
I assumed it would always be that way, too.
Did you get the first harpoon again today, Fam?
You betcha!
Turan and the Ades Federation
were set to sign a peace accord
when Premier Luscinia Hez appeared,
leading a Federation fleet.
I can't believe they betrayed Turan,
pretending to want peace...
Gisey! Look!
"The Winged Maiden"...
Turan's flagship, the Lasas!
Take the two princesses alive!
Kill all the rest!
I've made up my mind!
I'm going to steal that ship!
Light signal from what appears
to be a Sky Pirate Vanship!
They're going to help us escape...
...in exchange for the Lasas?!
That's nonsense! Sky Pirate scum!
Okay, guys! Let's stir 'em up our usual way!
Roger that, First Harpoon!
She's attacking head-on!
And you people call yourselves
soldiers of the Augusta?!
Here we go!
Spin!
Clear #4 depth charge
and every last smoke bomb!
Fire everything!
Now let's blow off the top-wing!
Th-They scuttled their ship?!
The Lasas survived thanks to Fam's strategy...
...but Millia was more than displeased.
My sister might not have any qualms,
but I refuse to accept this nonsense!
That's right. Millia said I can
address her on a first-name basis.
It makes me happy,
but it's kind of embarrassing.
I'm still not used to it; I really
admire her as a princess and all.
--May I come in?
--Yes!
A letter to your family?
Y-Yes. We got permission
to make outside contact.
Oh?
Maybe I should write them something too, then!
I owe a lot to your family, after all!
Princess Millia...
"Princess"?
Luscinia was bent on conquering
the royal city of Iglasia.
My sister went after him to try to stop him,
after sending Fam and me to Iglasia without her.
Let's meet again in Iglasia.
Please be careful, Sister.
What happened to the Lasas?!
But, unable to keep her promise,
my sister fell into Luscinia's clutches.
Where is my sister?! Release her at once!
Have you heard of the "Exiles"?
The Exiles are detestable ships...
In the cataclysmic days of yore,
they served as emigrant vessels
to help people flee this world and carry
them into the furthest reaches of the sky.
And once the calamitous times were over,
they nonchalantly returned.
But there was no longer any land to be given
to those who had abandoned
and fled the suffering world.
You people should never have returned.
Let my sister go!
"That which is born from
the blue surface of water..."
I don't know what transpired or
what happened to my sister's body.
But I do know it resulted in
the worst possible outcome...
An Exile...?!
Don't shoot!
I was utterly powerless.
I lost my kingdom and family,
and did nothing but weep like a child.
And I completely lost it
when someone took off
with one of my sister's treasured mementos.
Don't tell me what to do!
I'm a Turan princess, you know!
You've never touched a
Vespa in your life, Princess.
You can't fly it! It's too much for you!
But... It belongs to my sister...
It belongs to my sister...
Get out of there!
Get out!
Absolutely not!
Don't get the wrong idea!
I want you to get out and move to the back seat!
Hurry!
I'll be your wings!
Fam was always there to help me.
Fam just couldn't ignore her.
Because she knew how
hard it is being all alone.
I heard you took her in
when she was just an infant.
"May the wind carry wings that are lost."
Help anyone in the sky who
needs help. It's a Sky Pirate rule.
"Return fallen wings to the sky."
That's another Sky Pirate rule.
I had always thought Sky Pirates
were a band of savages...
How wrong I was.
Here.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Gisey! Millia!
What's going on?
I'm gonna go steal Silvius
the Reaper for Millia now!
Correction-- Fam is something else entirely.
I know we need military might to rebuild Turan,
but why must she always
go for such big scores?
My bad feeling turned out to be right...
Playing war, are you?
I think Tatiana was testing us at the time.
Now that you've seen the Silvius,
we can't let you leave alive.
You were in that red Vanship.
We could return you to the sky,
if you'll agree to help us.
What do you want out of us?
Go steal some Ades Federation ships--
one for each year you've been alive.
Too much for you kids to handle?
All right, then! We'll swipe fifteen for you!
We'll put an entire fleet together
if we have to, for Millia!
Fam always has us on our toes.
Yes...
We were tasked with hunting and
capturing fifteen Federation battleships.
It sounded like an outrageous undertaking,
but they managed to capture
a ship in the blink of an eye.
Meanwhile, Millia created a
Turan kingdom inside the Silvius.
What's with that outfit?!
I-I had no choice! It's part
of the plan to rebuild Turan!
Congratulations on establishing
a refugee government!
Isn't this great?!
What's wrong, Millia?
I was just thinking how pathetic it is
that this is the best I can do now...
Millia...
I don't know if I can really
rebuild Turan like this...
But this is honest-to-goodness
territory you acquired all by yourself!
This table is just the start!
Soon you'll have all of the Silvius!
And then it'll be time to take Turan back!
It wasn't much territory at all.
But it was my first step.
I must protect Turan, until the day
I'm reunited with my sister.
Our Skyfish hunt progressed smoothly,
until only one catch remained.
We're here for Skyfish!
Some huge ones are headed this way!
The battleships Ades is transporting...!
So you're after 'em, too?
It's gonna be a fierce battle, though!
Good tailwinds!
The best position! Good going, Gisey!
The first harpoon is mine!
The Jagannath...!
Ades' 3rd Fleet?!
The final Skyfish was an Ades Federation trap.
I was completely useless,
faced with their new, unknown weapon...
--Time to leave.
--All that for nothing...
Fam. We should go, too...
Don't be so glum! We'll just
find new prey to go after!
"I'm a failure as a Navi."
"I want to go home."
Distracted by these feelings, I never
realized we were being followed.
Their real target had been the Silvius...
...and me.
Commence fire!
--All ships, commence firing!
Fire!
Enemy has taken siege formation!
We're completely surrounded!
Tear through!
1st and 2nd Squads!
All ships, train guns on target!
Roger that! Training guns!
Target acquired...!
Wh-What?!
Distance to Glacies border, 40!
Enemy fleet deploying ahead!
Torpedoes incoming!
Down trim, 30! Take us into the clouds!
Target is descending... into the clouds!
Enemy has evaded torpedoes!
You can't, Fam! We're in the middle of a battle!
Retrieve the Vanships!
Th-That's what I tried to tell her, too...
The Skyfish hunt!
Skyfish hunt...?
Yeah! The Skyfish hunt!
I'm gonna fulfill my promise
to you once and for all!
This is the perfect chance!
Don't you agree, Captain?!
We can't retrieve you during battle.
You'll have to make it back on your own.
Fam wanted to do whatever she could to help,
and I found myself completely
caught up in the desire to assist.
The Anshar?!
She's chasing the Silvius! Not if  we can help it!
--Millia!
--Right!
Please...
Hit it!
A direct strike to a ship's Claudia Unit
to stop her dead in the sky...
She had managed to pull off
what I was never able to...
--Welcome back!
--Way to go!
She managed to take down the Anshar?
You guys are amazin'!
Princess Millia!
I was moved to tears!
Congratulations, Fam.
You were amazing too, Princess Millia...
You... finally managed to pull it off...
I didn't feel fit to be Fam's Navi.
So I decided to leave the Silvius.
You're really gonna leave?
I can't fly without you, Gisey.
Then just ask Princess Millia.
She has thorough knowledge
and good judgment.
Unlike me.
I'm not fit to be your Navi, Fam...
You're better off with Princess Millia.
--But you're amazing, Gisey!
--I'm not. I'm nothing...
Don't talk like that!
What would you know?!
I lashed out unfairly. I was pathetic.
I'd only been thinking of myself...
--I...!
I want to cheer Fam up!
I don't like it when Fam is feeling down either!
My jumbled-up feelings all came together.
To have Fam smile...
That was what I really wanted.
Gisey!
Fam... I'm...
Welcome back!
I'm home!
I felt the same way.
I'm open!
I want to make them-- and people
all over the world-- smile again...
--Gisey!
--Right!
...by holding another Grand Race someday!
I feel like with Fam, dreams that
seem crazy are actually possible!
Yes! With Fam, they are!
Fam is all we can think about, huh?
Yeah!
Gisey! Millia! It's time to eat--
Oh! What are the two of you up to?!
--Oh, are you heading out?
--Yeah.
I'm gonna go pay those prodigal girls a visit.
I'm going to stay aboard
the Silvius with Fam and Millia.
To defeat the Federation
and hold another Grand Race...
That is our dream!
And Fam Fan Fan is going to win it, of course!