We come to this holy
place to seal a pact
between two great peoples...
With this sacred water...
drawn from the blue
depths of the Hole,
source of the Grand Lake...
I celebrate and bear
witness to this covenant
between Anatoray and Turan.
Representing Anatoray-Disith...
Commander of the Vanguard
Unit... Vincent Alzey.
On behalf of the
government of Anatoray...
I hereby make
covenant with Turan.
Millia il Velch
Cutrettola Turan...
As proxy for Turan... and
for its regent Liliana...
I hereby make covenant
with Anatoray.
Illegal Move.
Whew...! My shoulders
are killin' me.
It was pretty nerve wracking...
Millia sure looked
beautiful, though.
She was every inch a princess
during the ceremony.
It's so good to see her
getting back to her old self.
Yeah, I agree...
She's one impressive girl.
Fam...! Gigi!
You actually did it...
You built her a fleet!
And on top of that,
you even got old Silvius
the Reaper on our side!
Looks like you might
be a rival, after all.
Your rival?! You wish!
--What, intimidated?
--Not even a little!
Well... we better head out.
We're gonna go scatter
these all over the place.
"Anatoray and Turan hereby
form an alliance...
Together, we will oppose
Federation invasions...
Come gather, fellow
citizens of the world...
Take a stand and fight
for your freedom."
This sounds great, you guys!
Doesn't it?!
Don't get excited.
It's non-alcoholic...
We're all countin' on
you to spread the word.
Yeah, we loaded
you up with gifts...
Just don't go crashing
from all the weight okay?
Thanks a lot...
The kids'll appreciate it.
Fair winds to you.
Fair winds to you!
Good tailwinds to you!
Tell everyone we say "hi"!
Drink up, me hearties!
My friends... the
Federation is mighty...
and so... we shall work to
strengthen our alliance...
We shall recruit others...
Together, we shall
be a bright flame...
burning hot enough to
consume the Federation...
May victory belong to us!
People of Anatoray.
You have my deepest gratitude...
When we had nowhere to turn...
you gave us hope...
I speak for all of
Turan when I say,
"I welcome Anatoray's
return home!"
Let us continue
side-by-side in this.
Together we will make this
world a bountiful one.
Dio.
Have you touched them
yet...? The clouds?
I'm so full!
No dessert, then?
Maybe later.
I can't move... my dress
has gotten too tight.
Please try some of the
coffee I made, Princess.
It's an Urbanus institution.
Sounds lovely, thanks.
Whoa, bitter...
Congratulations, Princess...
Looks like all your hard
work has finally paid off.
Thanks in part to you...
I promise I will
uphold the agreements
you reached with my sister.
Our main forces haven't
arrived... just us so far...
We are still lacking
in military might.
Which explains why your
activities have been covert.
Since you know this world,
I could use your advice...
Who else would you recommend
we bring into our alliance
in the immediate future?
In terms of sheer
military muscle,
the northern nation of
Glacies is right at the top...
Unfortunately,
they're isolationists,
and have cut off all relations
with outside peoples.
And if we add to that,
the fact the Silvius commenced
hostilities with them...
Gettin' nations with
such different cultures
and traditions ta see
eye-to-eye is no easy task.
Tell ya the truth,
even us Sky Pirates
have trouble managin'
ironclad solidarity.
So this is what they mean
by an "acquired taste."
Who is this girl?
Let me introduce you...
This is Alvis Hamilton.
No need to be scared...
My name's Fam Fan Fan...
but just Fam is fine...
and these two are...
Oh, I'm Millia.
And next to her's my navi, Gigi.
It's nice to meet you.
Alvis here can control
the Anotaray Exile...
She's a very special young girl.
She controls it?!
There's no need to be
frightened, Millia...
Al happens to be a
dear friend of mine.
She's already lost
much in her life...
and endured many hardships...
But despite what's
happened to her,
Al is always
considerate of others...
a trait she has in
common with your sister.
Dio explained everything
to me, Princess...
about how you and
your sister are like me.
What are you talking about?
The ability to activate one
of the Exiles is passed down
through the women of
the Turan royal family...
From mother to daughter...
from daughter to granddaughter.
The dormant Exiles are
in orbit above us...
But they will descend to
the surface when called.
Only one female
has this ability...
Should she die,
the power passes on
to the female closest
to her in age...
Sometimes her daughter...
sometimes her younger sister.
But I don't have
any power like that.
Which means we know
your sister still lives.
That's amazing news!
Oh no!
Federation ships approaching.
All hands to battle stations...
Federation ships approaching!
All hands to battle stations!
Acoustics ID'ed... Federation
ship Impetus approaching.
Luscinia is here?
Flags spotted!
Looks like the Premier...
and a Turan princess!
A... Turan princess?
Lily, is it you?
Princess Liliana is still alive?
I can hardly believe it!
Did the Federation
take her captive?
It really is you!
Look at that...!
It is Princess Lily.
Lily! I'm so happy
you're all right!
Millia... Thank you for
all of your hard work.
And Fam, Giselle...
Thank you for all the help
you've provided my sister.
Oh... Sure!
Uh... Lily--
Are you the commander
of Anatoray's military?
Vincent Alzey, Princess...
I speak with the authority
of the Anatoray government.
You also aided my sister...
My humble gratitude.
I did what anyone in
my position would.
Hear me, beloved
people of Turan.
You have endured much and still
held fast to your loyalty...
It fills me with a fierce pride.
I am happy to say that...
at last... your struggles
will be rewarded.
To fulfill my late
father's aspirations,
I have made a decision.
I, Liliana il Grazioso Merlo
Turan hereby assume control.
Last Exile.
To fulfill my late
father's aspirations,
I have made a decision.
I, Liliana il Grazioso Merlo
Turan hereby assume control.
As your ruler,
I proclaim to you all:
the fighting between Turan and
the Federation is at an end.
Meet Luscinia Hafez...
The Ades Federation Premier.
Turan has brokered a truce
with the Federation
for lasting peace.
Once unified under Ades rule,
the world will enter an age of
tranquility and prosperity
such as it has never known.
A truce...? What?
I can't believe it!
Your sister just sold Turan out
to the Federation!
People of Turan...
Her Majesty, Liliana,
has spoken the truth...
I ask you to heed her
words and rest easy.
As of this day,
the Federation hereby
guarantees your protection.
Yes...! Hurrah for peace!
Long live Her Majesty,
Liliana! Hurrah!
What's going to happen
to the fleet now?
From the look of it,
Princess Lily's going to
commandeer the whole thing.
Wait, you mean she's
taking it away from Millia,
just like that?
No! That's not right!
We built that fleet ourselves!
For Millia!
That was quite a
masterful performance.
You speak in such grand terms
like unification
and protection...
yet, all I hear is "domination."
I've received reports regarding
Anatoray's terrorist activities.
Are you the captain
of the Silvius?
A woman. I'm surprised.
Your ability to thwart our
fleet was impressive...
Though, clearly, your
actions were the result
of a grave misunderstanding...
Relinquish the Silvius and
swear us your allegiance...
Do so and I'll
overlook your crimes.
And should we refuse?
You have ten minutes...
Consider carefully.
Please, Lily...!
This is madness!
Have you forgotten what
these people did to Turan?!
I do this for the good
of the whole world.
What are you going to do
with the fleet we assembled?
Millia... Your temporary
rule is over...
Hold your tongue
and come with me now.
No, Lily, I'm not going
anywhere with you...
This is Turan's territory.
I hoped it would
not be this way...
I therefore strip
you of your title...
From this day on, you are
neither Turan royalty,
nor my sister.
How could you?!
The next time we meet will
be on the field of battle.
Luscinia is controlling
Lily somehow,
it's the only explanation!
If he wasn't around,
I'm sure she'd listen to reason.
That's it! I just need to find a
way to steal her back from him!
It will only take one
order from Liliana,
and Millia's fleet will
be turned against us.
Even with Millia
herself still aboard?
I assume they will
still follow my sister.
Shall we turn the
Silvius over to them?
I don't believe for a second
they would leave us
unharmed if we did.
What should I do? It's hopeless.
Losing heart isn't
going to help anything.
Our alliance was
with you alone...
Far as we're concerned,
you represent Turan, not her.
Yeah, she's right, Millia.
As long as you're
aboard the Silvius,
the Turan refugee government
will still exist.
Orders from the Impetus.
Prepare for an immediate
attack on the Silvius.
What?! We cannot assault a
ship with Lady Millia onboard.
Princess Liliana!
Listen well...
I retitle this vessel
the Turan flagship, Lasas...
Accordingly, it is now
under my direct command.
Yummy!
Cake...! Cake!
Do we get to eat stuff
like this all the time
just for being friends
with Anatoray?
Yeah, I think that's
the general idea.
Then they sound like the
best allies we could have!
Best allies ever! Lots of cake!
How're the leaflets
coming along?
We're printing 'em out
as quick as we can.
Think I'll try to get
a little shut-eye
'til they're ready, then.
Federation's Third
Fleet spotted!
Target has been destroyed!
Accuracy was passable,
I suppose.
I bet they're starting
to panic now...
The little fools
thought they could relax
as long as they stayed above our
battleships' altitude limits.
Pirate scum...
It's time to punish them
for their detestable ways.
Dirty traitors...!
Why are you shooting...?
I caught those Skyfish
for Millia. They're hers!
Give cover for the
Urbanus' withdrawal.
Roger that!
Commence firing, now!
I'm relieved to see
you're unharmed.
Full combat speed...!
Withdraw!
Commence fire!
But, Your Majesty, Lady Millia
is aboard that ship!
Fate can be unkind.
Now open fire!
This can't be happening.
It's wrong!
Fam! Where are you going?
To get Princess Lily back!
Wait!
Turan ship dead ahead.
Cutting off our retreat...
Change course now!
Not enough time!
Full speed, then...!
We'll ram them if we have to!
Urbanus has withdrawn
from battle.
Good. Now it's our turn
to get out of here...
Continue firing at will.
Full speed ahead!
Number five turret!
What're you doing?
Don't stop firing!
Number five turret!
Respond...!
Number Five...!
Number Five, come in!
Has it taken enemy fire?
Negative!
Gimme visual confirmation.
Stop running!
Don't worry, Millia...
I'll have Princess Lily
back here in no time.
She isn't under anyone
else's control...
I could see it in her eyes...
I know she meant it.
She's not going to
listen to me about this.
She has to.
It's him again.
Dio?
Go... Protect Millia.
Get as far as you can! Hurry!
Okay... Let's go!
But he...
See you guys later!
What the...?!
We have intruders onboard!
Heavy crew casualties!
Seal bulkheads...!
Confirm intruders' location.
Don't let them into
the engine area!
Sounds like snakes
have slithered aboard.
I must protect Turan territory!
You are going to
sit tight and behave!
I won't let anyone
take our land!
No response from turrets
number three and four.
Bridge! Bridge!
Fam, Millia, and Giselle
requesting permission
for takeoff!
Permission granted...
The Silvius is currently
fending off an enemy intrusion.
Take Princess Millia
to a safe location...
And don't worry... We'll
come to collect you later.
Roger!
Don't go gettin' shot down.
Same goes for you!
Right!
The captain sent this.
Fair winds to you!
Thanks...! Good tailwinds!
Fire at will, men!
Captain, they've taken
over the engine area.
Then we've been defeated.
So, a scion of the white...
Then you're from
the Guild, as well...
I've heard of
identical bodyguards
who serve a Maestro...
but I've never seen them.
What's going on?
Did the Silvius go under?
We got incoming
at seven-o'clock!
Climbing!
Turan's future is
our responsibility...
We'll have to make
certain we work hard, too.
Then I'll study a whole bunch
and get super smart
so I can help you!
While I do appreciate
your ambitions for it--
Here, Daddy... For good luck.
I'm'onna fly... and
everyone's gonna smile...
just like they are today.
Look at this, little one...
This, my Sara, is the world
you shall protect one day.