Whoa!
Get outta the way!
Whoa--look out!
Quit it, René!
Just wait...! When Gigi gets
back, I'm gonna tell on you!
Gonna tell on you!
It's not the same...
I miss 'em... I sure hope
they make it home soon.
Uhh... They are comin'
home, aren't they?
Of course they will, Adele...
I know it... Gigi and
Fam will be fine...
The wind's on their side.
The Fuchs and the
Frohlich are plummeting.
How many ships are remaining?
We're down to twenty-five!
All ships, forward...!
The Grand Exile must
not be taken down!
The Silvius is aground!
The Vanship squadron?
They've all departed.
Then we have no one left
to help the Silvius...
That changes our focus.
We'll neutralize its main
guns from the inside...!
Forward full!
News from the infiltration team?
They're still locked in battle!
No recent contact...!
Fam... Giselle, please...
So it's you... I'm impressed.
What have you done to her?!
She's simply resting...
She is exhausted, nothing more.
I can assure you,
she is in no danger.
You're lying! How dare you?!
Fam!
The Augusta will
awaken once more...
and this world will
be a changed place.
This is wrong...!
It's not what Sara wanted!
She would never use this ship
to cause more
destruction and suffering!
She would never hurt people!
Damn it, can't shake these guys!
Heine?!
It's okay! I'm fine...!
Engine and fuel lines
are still green... Go!
We Sky Pirates are
stronger than you think!
There's so many!
Do not break formation.
Let's secure Fam
an escape route!
[in Russian]
I can't take any more of this!
Please, no more...!
No more death!
This ship was not actually
built to cause destruction...
In fact...
It was created to
soar through the sky.
Really?
During the Great Cataclysm...
this was centuries
upon centuries ago...
the Exiles were built...
so some could flee this world.
Your repatriate ancestors
built these ships...
and the people they abandoned,
dreamed of only one thing.
Wings to break free
of this broken world...
and soar freely
through the sky...
An Exile that would
surpass all others.
Despite everything...
we held fast to that dream.
Generation after generation.
And you think this Exile is
going to fulfill that dream?
Just look at her...
She's still incomplete...
She was abandoned
a long time ago...
They left her, unfinished...
and forgotten.
Indeed.
That's why I'm here...
to see it completed...
I have but one goal...
To unify the world...
to bring lasting peace...
In Sara's name.
Understand...?!
I'll do what I must!
More artillery-loading acoustics
coming from the Grand Exile,
over ten tons again!
Target orientation holding at
one-hundred-ninety-one degrees.
He's intent on taking out
Turan... Most unfortunate...
...given the Silvius'
current immobility.
All hands, brace
for impact, now...!
Ready bow-mounted cannons
and back us out, full reverse!
Fire!
Forward guns operational!
Secondary lateral guns ready!
You heard 'em.
Go flanking speed...!
Catch up with the fleet!
Let's take out the
Grand Exile's artillery!
With the power of
the Grand Exile,
Premier Luscinia will bring
peace unto this world...
And our task is to
pave the way for him!
Gloria, Augusta!
It's true. The Premier's
method will undoubtedly produce
the quickest results...
Oh, well...
Guess I'm still too wet behind
the ears to know any better.
Output dropping!
We've lost artillery battery B!
Third and Fourth Squads
have fallen away...
Unable to maintain formation!
There comes a point
when you must realize
that life is about more than
blindly following orders.
What we do now, we do
for Augusta Sara...
Don't give up...!
All ships, charge!
Gloria, Augusta!
Your dream of another
Grand Race is noble...
However... as I am
certain you are aware...
Not even Augusta Farahnaz
could realize that dream...
Ideals alone cannot
change this world.
Yeah, I know... I know that.
This is the real world...
and things aren't as simple
as we want them to be.
You can't just chase
after your dreams...
Blind faith will
do nothing for you.
I... I know that now!
But still...
It's my dream...
and I will chase it!
How can I not...?
The Grand Race has always
been what's guided me.
It's my singular wish...
And it's kept me aloft
when nothing else could.
It was a gift...
given to me by the brave people
who made that first
Grand Race a reality.
Don't you see...?!
I will never stop flying!
Fire time-delay torpedoes!
We'll use the ship as a shield!
Let's clear a path for
the Empress Sophia.
Concentrate all our fire
on the enemy cannon!
I'm right... they're not
offensive weapons...
So what are they?
What now? Should we try to
make a temporary retreat?
Fam will bring Sara out...
I know she will.
All right then... Train all
guns on their interior walls!
Draw the tentacles'
attention to us! Fire!
Maybe you're right.
Maybe all my hopes and dreams
will fall apart like last time.
Maybe nothing will change...
Maybe all the hatred
and sorrow will continue.
Even if that happens,
I will keep flying.
Because I know... eventually...
someone will make
the dream come true.
I admit, I'm glad you came.
Where I'm going...
she cannot accompany me.
It is time.
Last Exile.
Something's blowing
apart on the enemy hull!
Coming from near the gun
that's about to fire!
What's happening?!
It's now spreading
throughout the entire ship
at tremendous speed.
I had it all wrong...
Those aren't guns...
They're enormous
propulsion engines.
Ah... that's what it's about.
You wanted to take
everyone into the sky...
So... You readied your
multitude of wings...
But sadly... it was
never meant to be.
Anyone know what the heck is
going on with this monstrosity?!
We've done all we can.
Damn... Everyone, follow me out.
Grand Exile structural
collapse at twenty...
twenty eight percent...!
Destruct-sequence accelerating.
Admiral! Our ships are
requesting your orders!
All hands... abandon ship.
We've reached the
end of our era...
All ships...
disarm immediately...
Obey the Joint Forces orders.
But, Admiral...!
It's what the Premier
himself wishes...
He issued these instructions
before he departed.
Guzel... please... I have
one favor yet to ask of you.
Sir?
Take this... Get it
to my granddaughter.
You knew this was
going to happen...
You knew from
the very beginning.
Luscinia!
No, wait...! Come with us!
For Sara! She doesn't want this!
She doesn't want anyone to die!
It will be all right...
Liliana said she didn't regret
the hand fate had dealt her...
having been born
as an Exile key.
Alauda and I feel
the same way...
Take care of Maestro Sara.
Luscinia!
Let's go!
After all this... all the
sadness and death!
Can't you at least take some
responsibility?! Luscinia!
Fam, we gotta go now!
Falling debris has increased
the load on our keel
by seventy percent...
We can't take much more!
Where's the rescue team?
Reports say they're
on their way out now.
And Sara?!
Still no word that the Augusta
has been successfully retrieved.
Fam...
Grand Exile descending!
Roughly two-point-five minutes
of operational altitude.
--It's the Senapati!
--What?!
Orang... follow!
Right, Sorush...
All ships, follow the Senapati.
Let's make a run for it!
We can't wait for the Augusta's
rescue team any longer...
Engines to max!
Take us away from the Exile!
I'm sorry.
Engines to max... now!
Straight for ten
seconds, then right!
Roger!
Liliana...
Were we right...?
Will the world change...?
Truly change...?
As we hoped it would?
Fam...
This engine's acoustic...
It's Fam!
Light signal from the Vespa...
"The Augusta has been
safely rescued!"
They're... back!
They did pretty well, huh?
The Augusta is safe!
Augusta... Thank goodness.
Hey, ya pulled
it off, Birdbrain!
Way to go!
Yeah, Fam...! Gigi!
Her sixteenth Skyfish sure
turned out to be a big one, huh?
Yeah.
Fam...! Giselle!
Sara! Sara!
You're awake.
What's going on...?
Where are we?
Sara!
Where's Vasant...? And
Luscinia...? Where are they?!
Please, Fam!
Where are they? Tell me!
So you're sure this
is all of them?
You aren't hiding any other
ships, I hope?
What, you don't trust us...?
Ades is completely on
board with disarmament.
Aw yeah...
...these guys use some
really great Claudia units.
Bet we can get a lot for 'em.
C'mon! Quit slacking,
you old geezers...!
Look out, comin' through!
There's still so much to do!
I wonder what we can
build with these Units.
I hear Turan's started using
'em for power generators.
With this sacred water,
drawn from the
blue depths of the Hole,
source of the Grand Lake,
I hereby celebrate and bear
witness to this covenant.
Please, allow me.
We have a pact...
among member nations...
We will coexist harmoniously...
We'll strive to uphold peace...
so that everyone may prosper.
After all these years,
the world is finally moving
in the right direction.
It is--because we're
all working together...
Although...
a number of Ades citizens
still seem to be
a bit anxious...
Orang... can I count
on you to help them?
Yes, Gloria, Augusta.
It's reassuring to have
you as our mediator...
I know you'll do well,
Premier Orang.
I will serve...
but it is Sorush who
should be filling this role.
But he...
Maybe I should learn
how to fly a Vespa.
That could be quite diverting.
You'd appreciate that,
Vasant... wouldn't you?
Young lady, I have
something for you.
What is it?
She looks just like you!
But, who...?
It's from Admiral Sadri...
He wanted his
granddaughter to have it.
Sadri...?
But... but I... I thought...
I broke his foot!
Fam...
Fam, what's the matter?
Hey, don't cry!
There's so much
we could've talked about...
questions I could've asked,
like about my mom...
So many potato pancakes
we could've shared...!
Luscinia...
I think that...
maybe you loved Lily.
Ah-ha...! There she is!
What are you doin'
out here, Dyan?
Fam?
How am I supposed to
brag about winning the race
if you don't even
compete in it...?
Now, come on.
You need to get ready.
Quit shoving her around!
If you don't have a ship,
you can borrow one of ours.
You remember...
I know you do...
The feeling of
the wind in your face!
The... wind?
Don't think
you'll beat us, though.
Yeah...!
Now... I won't take
no for an answer!
Wait up!
Claus...! Lavie!
Hi, Al!
See...? I told you
they were interesting.
I told ya, we're
all gonna be in it!
Will you never give up?
Fam!
D'you think...
that I'll ever fly again?
Immelman...
Of course you will, silly!
We'll all fly together...
right, Dio?
Yeah... Sure will!
Fam...! Giselle!
Good luck out there!
Careful, Princess!
Hey! Thanks!
We got this, just watch!
Oh...? You do?
Dyan!
Just leave us alone!
Well...? Ready, Luciola?
Everyone...!
At last, it's time...!
Welcome to the
Second Grand Race!
People of the world...
Thank you...
It's because of you
all of this is possible...
It's a day of joy!