Come on! Hurry up, you two!
All right.
Ugh! I'm going.
Fam...! Wait for me!
Good afternoon,
fellow citizens...
This shall be a glorious day,
one to be remembered.
May this celebration of peace
and friendship be spoken of
with joy for
generations to come.
We have sworn before
the Grand Lake...
From this day forward, let
ours be a world of harmony.
And now... Let the
First Grand Race begin.
Yay!
Grand Race... Hurray!
Backward pawn.
Atamora...! Kaiser!
Are you our cheerleaders today?
Mm-hm!
We're countin' on you,
so you better leave 'em
in your dust, okay?
Who do you think you're
talkin' to, huh?
If you lose you have to
scrub all the toilets
in Kartoffel for an entire year!
I accept those terms,
young lady, but if we win,
you have to start
eating your carrots.
No fair! Carrots are yucky!
Here, Daddy, this is
for you... For good luck.
Thanks!
Do I get one, too?
Yep...! Here's yours, Kaiser.
Ooh! We'll be unbeatable now!
To hell with you people!
Quit acting like
you own this world
just 'cause you and your
kind weren't good enough
to get a ride on an Exile.
Don't give me that...!
It's your people bargin' in,
takin' other folks'
land from them!
Hey, if it's a fight
you're after--
The hell are you...? Let me go!
Cool it, loudmouth...
Do you wanna sully
this historic day?
What do those guys wanna
go and start a fight for...?
That's the opposite of what
the Grand Race is about.
Everyone will calm
down eventually...
In fact, that's
part of the reason
for holding the event today.
Time for the second race of
the final qualifying round.
Marvelous!
Millia.
King Turan, I bid you welcome.
I am so pleased
you could attend.
Augusta FarahnAz.
Today's celebration has been
a truly memorable
experience for all.
We are honored to make
your acquaintance.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
How do you do...?
I'm happy to meet Turan's
adorable princesses.
I'm Liliana, your Highness.
I'm Millia.
I'm sorry, dear.
Did they startle you?
So, uh... are these
your bodyguards?
Yes. But you needn't fear them.
They are angels
who have come from
the land of the white
sky to protect me.
Angels?
--Kaiser's in the lead!
--Go, Dad!
Come on! Show 'em
what you're made of!
Careful, Fam!
Go! Go-go!
Wow, your dad is awesome.
He's flying the
latest Notos model...
It has twenty percent more
engine power than other ships.
Wow, Gigi...! You're so smart!
Oh! That's an Ades
Federation Heavy Vanship.
People still fly those
clunky old things?
Don't talk like that
about the Shaharz!
Please...! That relic's no
match for our Vanships.
Better watch it,
dirty Sky Pirate.
Now, now, children. Not so fast.
Why don't you try some
treats from Her Majesty?
--Can we have some, too?
--Sure!
All right! Thanks, Ades dude!
See? We're not so bad!
--Awesome!
--Don't hog 'em all!
Hey, now!
There's no need to push.
Indeed, I agree...
By working tirelessly on
negotiations with other lands,
Augusta Farahanaz
has finally been able
to make world peace a reality.
Thanks to her unwavering
conviction and warm soul,
the world has come
together at last...
Not just anyone could have
accomplished what she has.
She is truly a remarkable woman!
What are you two
doing over there?
Is there something the matter?
Millia...
Luscinia... Careful,
you're frightening her.
What should I do, then?
You could try
smiling, for a start.
I see.
Luscinia.
That was a nice attempt...
but it needs some work.
In your next training session,
we'll have to go over
how to smile again.
The history of Vanships
has quite a bit in common
with the history of the world...
Vanships...? How so?
Just look at them, dear...
For years, they were
all so different...
Only now are they beginning
to be standardized...
But today, they
have come here...
all these different Vanships
at this sacred lake...
soaring together
through the same sky.
Fellow citizens of the world,
striving for the same goal...
unified by the desire to see
their dreams become reality...
Yes, they'll occasionally
still fight each other...
but there's respect now...
because they can
see what they share.
My hope is that the people
will see their lives
as an extension of
today's celebration.
Turan's future is
our responsibility...
We'll have to make
certain we work hard, too.
Then I'll study a whole
bunch and get super smart
so I can help you!
Sounds lovely... Thank you.
So that's what
Glaciens look like...
I've never seen one before.
No one said they were
so good looking...
Ooh...! And look at
those girls from Notos!
Come on, Sorush!
We are on duty, you know.
Come on. Nothing's
gonna happen today...
Relax... You should try
observing the beautiful scenery,
like I am...
All these girls!
The Augusta's truly great.
Be quiet...
Do not dare sully the Augusta's
noble ideals with your lechery.
Whoa, whoa, I'm just kidding...
You can be a real prude, Orang.
And you can be a real
loudmouthed fool!
There we have it, folks!
Kaiser and Atamora of Kartoffel
advance to the finals!
Oh, forgive me...
It's an old habit.
Bracelets like that are
used to count prayers,
aren't they, Your Highness?
Yes... although...
For the moment, it serves
a different purpose...
I use it to count all the
sins that I have committed.
Your sins?
Millia?
Last Exile.
I wonder if maybe...
my family might be
here somewhere.
You playing hide-and-seek?
Shh!
--Princess Millia?!
--Princess...?
--That way!
--Right...!
--Princess?
--Hello? Princess!
Don't tell anyone!
Huh? Oh... Why?
Please, just don't!
'Kay!
Hello, little one.
Have you seen a girl about
your age pass this way?
Nope! Sorry.
I see...
--Princess Millia!
--Princess?!
--Please answer us, Princess!
--Oh, do stop hiding!
I think they're gone.
Thank you so much!
These are for you!
So long!
See ya!
Yashbal finishes first!
And advances to the finals!
Your behavior is inexcusable!
Have you any idea how
much you worried everyone,
running off on
your own like that?
But, Lily...
I don't want to hear excuses...
You're a Turan princess,
and you need to act like one.
Do you understand me?
Yes, I'm sorry...
Go easy on her, Liliana...
This is a day of joyous
festivity for all...
Surely you can understand
Millia's desire to make merry.
You pamper her too much, Father.
Princess Liliana...
I think that will be enough.
Your sister seems suitably
regretful of her actions,
don't you think?
Oh... Sorry.
Hurry along. The final
race is about to begin.
Oh yeah...! Right!
Come along, Millia.
Let's go watch.
I, ah...
I thank you, sir.
Right...
Fam! Fam!
Gigi!
Where'd you run off to? The
final race is about to start!
I guess it was pretty silly...
thinking I might find 'em here.
Oh, Fam...
Well... let's grab our seats.
Hey, I almost forgot...! Look!
What is this?
Candy?
It's so pretty!
I was pleased to
see, Luscinia...
that you helped Princess
Liliana without any prompting.
Sadly, he still has
moments of ineptitude.
Alauda.
It is the truth...
Regrettably, Princess
Millia views him
with quite an extreme
degree of fear.
Oh...? Is that what led to
Millia's sudden disappearance?
I apologize.
You think you can act
all high and mighty
just 'cause you
got decent marks?
What is going on, soldier?
Augusta!
She doesn't deserve the honor
of presenting the bouquet.
Chaos good-for-nothing,
she's only alive because of
Your Majesty's kindness.
Be on your way.
Y-Yes, Your Majesty!
Are you all right, miss?
Augusta Farahnaz...
Please, Your Majesty...
I truly respect you...
From the very bottom
of my heart... I do...!
And your cause...!
To unite the world and
end the fighting at last...!
To make peace...!
Please rise.
Thank you, soldier...
I hope you will continue
to lend me your support.
The world will be better for it.
I... yes!
That young soldier
was from Chaos...?
We annexed them so long ago,
yet this still happens?
I am afraid many difficulties
lie on the road ahead.
Even with peace
treaties in place,
the world will still
be far from united.
Until the nations can forget
the pain of bloody wars,
hatred and discrimination
will never fully disappear.
I hope that girl
and those like her
someday live in a
world of acceptance.
But we have many
challenges yet to overcome.
You are the very
cornerstone of this world.
While I do appreciate
your ambitions for it...
Majesty... we cannot lose you
in your efforts to achieve
worldwide harmony.
Luscinia is correct in this...
Without you, the world
would be utterly lost...
cast adrift... as would we...
Alas, there is still so much
good work to be done...
and precious little
I can do myself...
Luscinia... Alauda.
Please, protect not only me...
but also the world I love.
It is a great honor...
and a great burden.
Augusta Farahnaz!
We came to get you...
Your Highness.
Dad and Kaiser took the lead!
And the winners of the
very first Grand Race
are Kaiser and
Atamora of Kartoffel!
They did it...! See Fam,
I told you Dad would win!
What is it?
Look how happy everyone is.
I'm gonna do this someday.
I'm 'onna fly... and
everyone's gonna smile...
just like they are today.
Everyone...
All the people I know...
And all the people I've
never even met before!
Awesome.
All right!
We won, kids!
--All right! Yay, Dad!
--That was awesome!
Look at this, little one.
My Sara.
There, there.
As winners of the first ever
Grand Race, I congratulate you.
Please accept this trophy.
Atamora...! Kaiser!
These children shoulder the
burden of our world's future.
They shall present
the victory bouquets.
Die, Farahnaz!
Th-Thank you...
for the bouquet...
It was... an... honor.
Kaiser!
Kaiser...! Kaiser!
Ades must pay!
The time for
retribution is at hand!
Stay back, Majesty.
--Father, no!
--Get out of here, Guzel!
Augusta! My lady!
My baby!
I've got her!
Atamora...! Kaiser!
Fam!
Atamora!
--Take him down!
--Vengeance!
Liliana!
Father...! Father!
I don't understand...!
How could they...? Why?
Why, Your Highness?
Oh...! Your Highness,
are you all right?
You're safe now...
you're safe...
Oh no, Your Highness!
Your Highness!
The dictator is dead...
It is done. My people...
you are avenged!
Farahnaz... Your Majesty...
White monster!
Kill you all... Who else?!
Luscinia...
I will protect you,
my lady Sara...
I will always keep you safe...
I promise... Always! I swear!
I'll kill them all...
Who else...? Who else?!
That's enough...
Hush... Luscinia.
Please...! Just let me die!
Let me die with her!
Why?
Why now...? Of all days,
how could this happen?
What have we gotten
ourselves into?!
And more importantly,
where are we?
Whoa! Who are you?
What's that language
you're speaking?
Hey! It's totally white outside!
Snow! Everything's
covered in snow!
Whoever you are, you're
covered in snow, too!