An emergency message
from the admiral.
That was sooner
than anticipated...
Though we are dealing with
the Amethyst of Chaos.
So, what now...?
Shall I return to
the capital on my own
and extract Augusta Sara?
Let's leave this in
Sadri's hands for now...
We have important
work to do here.
Our success... will put
an end to the fighting.
Triangulation.
It appears Kumari,
Batos, Reetus,
and a few other
repatriate provinces
have already united in revolt...
alongside the remaining
Glacies forces
and several Sky Pirate camps.
There are also rumors that
the survivors of Turan
have rallied around
Princess Millia.
Vasant's move is
bold and decisive...
I must give her that.
The status of the Exiles?
We've succeeded in rendering
the Glacies Exile...
completely inoperable.
Good, meaning there's no chance
the rebel forces
can make use of it.
In a way, this rebellion has
actually benefited us...
All potential opposition
has been uncovered
in one fell swoop.
The rest is simple...
We take them out.
So that is the
premier's true goal.
It seems they've
beaten us to the draw...
Creating a grand
Anti-Federation alliance
to oppose the atrocities
Luscinia has committed
in the name of
world peace...
That's what we had
hoped to accomplish
by allying ourselves with Turan.
Likely, our announcement of that
alliance spurred them on...
We got the ball
rolling for them.
We gave them the
momentum they needed...
And now we must fulfill
our end of the bargain...
However... We can't make a move
with Ades right on our doorstep.
That would endanger
our mission here.
Our duty is to protect
this wheat-filled land...
no matter what happens.
Then we'll just have to hold out
until Lady Sophia returns.
Yes...
--Look, Princess Millia is here!
--We love you, Princess Millia!
Long live Princess Millia!
Hooray for the princess!
Long live Turan!
The Turanians are
excited to see her.
Of course they are.
They're pinning all their
hopes on this joint rebellion.
It still bothers me, though.
They virtually ignored her
when she was opposing
the Federation on her own.
Aw, what do they know?
They're a buncha
birdbrains, that's all.
Federation General Vasant
is behind this...
but I'm not sure we can
trust her... Should we?
As things stand,
we're powerless.
If there's dissent brewing
within the Federation,
we should do what we can
to use it to our advantage.
Like they say, "yer enemy's
enemy is your friend."
And if things do
start to get hairy...
we'll grab the princess and get
outta here as fast as we can.
Right!
Princess, Lady Vasant
has arrived.
We have been expecting you.
And so, in the name of
the newly established
Anti-Luscinia Joint Forces...
I welcome you all.
Vasant... That can't be right!
Luscinia has spent
all these years
fighting for the
sake of the people!
My people.
Yes, but it is the way he
fights that is the problem.
He has expanded the war...
killing far more people than
necessary for our objective
and plunging the entire
world into a vast whirlwind
of turmoil and suffering...
His sins are beyond imagining
and utterly unforgivable.
Luscinia is a tyrant...
His methods will never make
your late mother's
dream of peace a reality.
Now, please...
I need your decision.
Augusta Sara.
Pardon the intrusion,
but Princess Millia
of Turan has arrived.
So this is what the Ades
palace looks like, huh?
Dull compared to Turan's.
Manners.
Fam!
She's not alone in that...
All the foreign visitors
say the same.
Please accept my apologies...
It was horribly rude for
her to say such a thing.
Not at all... there is
no need to apologize...
Morvarid stands
in memory of those
who survived the great
cataclysm so many years ago.
After the lakes froze over
and the earth grew sterile,
this remained the
only habitable area...
It was the last
bastion for those
who were abandoned
by the Exiles.
To this day, our capital
rests on this land
so that we may never forget
that time in our history.
Now, come this way, if you will.
The Augusta awaits.
--She really is just a kid!
--Come on, Fam!
I can't help it if
I'm surprised...
I mean, I knew she was young,
but I had no idea--
Child or not, I am the Augusta.
Yes, I'm still young...
very young...
In many ways I'm powerless...
I understand that.
But... even so...
I am still the Augusta!
I represent the Ades people.
I fight for them.
I'm sorry!
My humblest apologies...
Augusta Sara... I beg your
forgiveness for her words.
You have my promise she will
be very thoroughly scolded
for her behavior here today.
Pardon me, Augusta.
Let us not forget that
these girls are victims
of Luscinia's war as well.
You must be exhausted
from your journey here...
I hope you find the
food to your liking...
Please take as much as you want.
Thank you, that's very kind.
--Yeah, thank you for the food!
--Thank you very much.
Turanian soldiers have begun
to hear of the alliance.
They are coming out
of hiding in droves
to stand with you
in this, Princess...
I happily return them to your
command, where they belong.
I am sure they will fight to
the best of their abilities
with you once again in a
position of leadership.
You'd be willing to do that?
Absolutely, I must admit we have
high hopes for you, Princess...
There aren't many who
could oppose Luscinia
as valiantly as you have
and live to tell of it.
Oh, well... I didn't
do it alone, of course.
You also received aid
from the Silvius...
I've heard all about
your work with them...
Do you know where they are now?
I'm afraid I don't...
We've completely lost
contact with them.
I was unaware of that.
I do wish Anatoray
could be here, though.
Oh, no... Please don't
concern yourself, Princess.
Your presence alone is more than
enough reassurance for us.
Luscinia still has many people
and resources at his disposal...
but we can no longer
overlook the atrocities
for which he is responsible.
The late Augusta Farahnaz
dreamed of a lasting peace...
That dream died ten years ago.
The time has come for us
to bring it back to life...
But to do so...
We must first
eliminate Luscinia.
Now, please, don't be shy...
Eat your fill...
These are the first
oranges of the season,
picked from a Notos oasis.
And, uh... what is this
stuff...? It's slimy!
Please, Fam!
No, it's fine... Not your
favorite dish, I take it?
That's millet porridge,
one of our staple recipes...
We eat it daily...
Everyone from the most humble
citizen to the Augusta herself.
Seriously?!
Soil capable of sustaining
a good crop of wheat
is difficult to
come by in our lands.
I am sorry...
...for calling you
a kid earlier.
You act a lot older,
and I can tell
you really do love your country.
As far as generals go,
Vasant seems pretty nice,
dontcha think?
Yeah.
We've all got a lot of
work ahead of us yet...
The Augusta is safe in
General Vasant's care...
but so far, these joint forces
are looking like a
pretty ragtag band.
I never realized there were
decent people on the Ades side.
but from what I can tell,
Sara seems like she'd
make a great ruler...
...if we can get
rid of Luscinia.
Dyan!
You made it through the battle!
Thank goodness...!
Does this mean you guys
are joining up, too?
Dyan?
[in Russian]
She says she cannot
be friends with me...
The sister of her enemy.
Dyan...
Last Exile.
Incredible... Vasant
inciting a revolt.
Well, the Chaos fleet
was essentially used
as a sacrificial pawn
during this latest battle.
What do you think?
About what, the premier?
Saying that sort
of thing out loud
is enough to earn a man a
speedy execution, you know.
--Sorush--
--Drop it, Orang...
...now.
Enter.
Orders to move out, sir...
as follows...
At dawn... you're to
make for Boreas...
...and then conquer it.
The fortress city of Boreas...
It is a key strategic point
positioned between
Ades and Glacies,
where the forces still loyal to
Luscinia are
currently stationed.
Located within Boreas are a
large-scale battleship dock...
...an abundant stockpile
of ammunition...
...and an ample number
of Claudia deposits.
On top of this, it is also
a major traffic artery...
All of the northeastern
Grand Lake routes
pass through its territory.
It is no exaggeration to say
that whoever controls this city
also controls the northern
shores of the Grand Lake.
What about the forces
remaining at the fortress?
Are they under
Luscinia's control?
They are not...
We have already called
for them to be placed
under the Augusta's
direct command.
The first thing we must do
is assemble our
respective teams of troops
in Boreas and fend
off Luscinia's forces.
Their long excursion
into Glacies
has stretched their
supply line thin.
As they start to weaken,
we will seek as many supporters
from around the world as we can.
When we're strong enough, we'll
take the fight to Luscinia.
Damaging Luscinia's forces at
Boreas could be key...
More people would
be likely to stand with us.
Forget this talk
of damaging them,
our goal should be
annihilation...
That tyrant likes bloodbaths
so let's treat him to one!
We'll make them bleed
for what they've done...!
We'll avenge our brethren
who were killed in Glacies!
Justice will be ours!
Victory will go to
the Joint Forces...
The only answer
to tyrants is death!
And a merciless execution
for the Turan witch
who helped them
with their massacre!
Death to the tyrants!
Death to the Turan witch!
Stop it!
Uh...
I mean, why don't we all just
take a deep breath...?
Surely there's no need for
us to be so bloodthirsty...
Sit down and be quiet weakling!
Me? A weakling...?
Sure, it's true I'm not
a soldier like you guys,
but that doesn't mean I--
Exactly! You are not soldier...
So keep your mouth shut!
But isn't peace what
brought everyone here...?
Honoring Farahnaz's wish...?
Making a world where another
Grand Race is possible?!
I'm not stupid.
I know we can't do that without
at least some fighting...
But you're talking about killing
just for the sake of revenge...
How will that help
us achieve our goal?
How does that make us
any better than them?!
You didn't have all your friends
and family slaughtered.
How could you
possibly understand?!
That's right!
What do you know about it?
--Sit down and be quiet!
--She knows nothing!
--Let it go, Fam. That's enough.
Wha--? Millia...
I'll be in contact
with you all tomorrow...
By that time,
I'll have the Boreas
defensive plans drawn up...
I thank you for
your cooperation.
I can't believe them!
Calm down, Fam.
Yeah, so maybe
I'm not a soldier...
...and maybe I can't
understand how they feel...
But I do know the vibe
in that room was all wrong!
I appreciate it, Fam.
Don't worry about me, though.
This is what matters now...
Defending Boreas Fortress from
Luscinia, whatever the cost.
Are you going to send
the Turan fleet out, too?
Good question... We have so
little time to get organized...
It's not going to be easy.
Even so, we must fight.
For Turan's future.
It'll work out, Millia.
You think?
If things don't go as planned,
there's always a chance you
could act as a mediator...
between the Joint Forces and
Princess Lily's people, I mean.
If that happens... you say the
word, and I'll be your wings.
Umm...
Really...?!
That was your father...?
The winner of the Grand Race?!
Uh... yes.
Wow...! That's incredible!
Yeah, you wouldn't believe it!
Atamora's team
was totally amazing,
like something out of a story!
And me and Gigi
have practiced really
hard to be as good as them.
You should see us, Sara!
I mean, Augusta...?
Please don't worry about it...
I want to hear
everything about that day.
Will you describe it for me?
They say the Grand Race was my
mother's dream brought to life.
A festive celebration meant to
bring happiness to the people.
Exactly!
That's what it did...
And that's why I'm gonna
make another one happen!
Oh, I know...!
Why don't you help us
hold a Grand Race?
You...
you want my help?
Of course...! Aw, man.
How did I not think of
this before now...?
With all of us working together,
it'll be perfect. Right?
Wow... You're
somethin' else, Fam.
Do you think that
could actually happen...?
A new Grand Race...?
Everywhere you
looked that day,
people had big smiles
on their faces!
Staring up at Atamora's Vespa,
the crowd was so happy!
Oh, do you know
what Vespas are...?
They're the small Vanships
we Sky Pirates use...
They may look tiny, but they
pack some serious power.
They're kinda like our secret
weapon, you know?
So, the total is
thirty-one battleships,
and six supply vessels...
That's a lot more
than I had expected!
There are many others out
there as well, still in hiding.
When they hear that you have
joined our cause, Princess,
I'm certain they will
all rush to our support.
That is... most encouraging.
After all this time...
We're finally returning
to our homeland!
I can't believe how
long it's been...
If only Grandfather
were here for this.
I heard when we're in Turan,
we'll get to eat
meat. Is it true?
I want meat too!
And you'll have it!
That's not all, either...
From now on,
there will be fish, too...
And you can eat as many
pastry treats as you want!
Yay!
Those are Gonians, aren't they?
Please, Princess...
Come away from there.
They need not trouble you.
They're the people who lived in
Turan before our
ancestors returned.
Yes, that's correct,
I'm afraid...
However, they are now a
part of the Joint Forces...
Unfortunately, that means we
can do nothing to stop them.
I've waited so long to plant
this seed where it belongs.
Oh, Lily... all these people...
Did you see them, too?
Oh, and I think my favorite
part of all was when
they pulled off a perfect
Split-S maneuver...
Like this, see?
Oh, wow...! Wow!
What is it? What do
you want to show us?
Just a bit further.
There, you see...?
That's my mother.
I don't remember her...
I was still little when
she passed away...
Just a baby,
too young for memories...
So this painting is all I have.
I'm sorry.
I want so badly to be like her.
You will, Sara. I know you will.
I'm scared.
I don't know why
Vasant and Luscinia
have to fight like this...
They've both worked so hard
and sacrificed so much
for the people of Ades.
And now this.
It's because I'm just a child...
Only a helpless little kid.
That's why...
That's why this is happening.
Luscinia was my mother's
bodyguard all those years ago.
When she died,
he blamed himself...
He was there, but he couldn't
do anything to stop it.
After it happened, he vowed to
protect me, no matter what...
and in order to do that, he
became Premier of all Ades.
All he wanted was to
create a peaceful world.
A world where I could
always be safe and happy.
Luscinia said he has
a dream of his own...
one that is very dear
and important to him.
He said there's a big,
ancient goddess
sleeping far away
to the north...
at the very edge of
where humans can go...
Luscinia wants to use
that goddess's power...
He says that, with her,
he can save the world.
The Augusta is
actually really nice!
Yeah! And she said we could
hang out again tomorrow!
Nice or not, she is still the
Augusta... Behave yourself.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
If you start teaching her
bad words or dirty jokes,
General Vasant might
have you executed.
Come on, Millia...
I would never do that.
Augusta?!.. What in
the world are you doing?!
Oops.
--Fam!