The Grand Exile was constructed
by the Ades Federation,
rightful rulers of this
world and all its lands...
It was designed to surpass
all else in its power.
I now have in my custody
the legitimate heir
and plenipotentiary over all
the inhabitants of this world.
In the name of MaestroSara,
I hereby declare...
As of this moment...
All acts of hostility
throughout the world...
are to come to an end.
All military forces
of all nations
will disarm at once
and surrender.
Those who refuse to comply
will be duly punished
by the Grand Exile.
All offensive weaponry will be
dismantled and destroyed...
Thus will begin an era of
true peace in this world.
He's gotta be kidding with this.
What's that bastard
know about peace?
If he wants an end
to the fighting,
maybe he should
stop making threats.
This isn't the peace
Sara dreamed about...
It's not what she wanted!
I can feel her... She's crying.
Triple rook.
Grand Exile's
position confirmed.
It's in Glacies, Grid G-7.
Moving south-southeast
by east at twenty knots!
Additionally, Admiral
Sadri's First Fleet
has taken formation ahead of it!
That murderer Luscinia does not
represent the Augusta's wishes.
All ships will focus on
eliminating the enemy fleet
arranged at the fore
of the Grand Exile.
Vanships will penetrate
its defenses...
We'll attempt to find the
Augusta... and rescue her.
Just can't wait to
scratch that itch
and get back in the action, huh?
It's the path we have to take.
We're the only ones who have
proper Vanship training
and can storm the ship.
I'm jealous. I wish
I could go play, too.
The Silvius is in
your hands now...
Support Commander-in-Chief
Millia the best you can, okay?
Right! Consider it do--
And you, Cecily...
Those ears of yours are going to
be vital inside the blizzard...
We're counting on you.
I'll do my best!
She's not the
only one, though...
As the new Turan witch,
can't you sense her, as well?
I'm needed here to
oversee our forces.
Dyan...
No, I can't...
My sister is dead.
I saw you kill her
with my own eyes.
I can't forgive that.
But, that doesn't
change the fact
that I have a duty to fulfill.
Duty...?
I must do whatever it takes.
I am Turan's ruler...
While my people survive,
I must lead them.
Don't you see...?
That is the task
I've inherited...
I must set my feelings aside.
Well, I hope you're ready.
They're all waiting.
To all those about to
confront the Grand Exile...
I fully believe...
The war ends with this battle.
Laying down our weapons
and surrendering now
might indeed end the
current hostilities...
as Luscinia claims...
But I ask you... could
we truly call that peace?
Gathered here today are people
from different nations...
different worlds, in fact.
Wherever we come from,
we share a common dream...
The dream of a peaceful,
prosperous future.
After all we've done, we know
we can change the world...
Not through force...
But through cooperation.
With compassion and
care for each other.
Let's build a better future...
Now... Let's do it together...!
What say all of you...?
Will you stand with me?!
Gigi... you know what...?
I really do still wanna
hold a new Grand Race.
It's not such a bad dream. So
many people were happy that day.
They were.
What's that for?
We will make it happen, okay?
You know the controls?
Crossing Glacies border.
ETA to the current location of
the Grand Exile is ten minutes.
Have we received any
word from the Silvius?
Unable to confirm.
Maintain formation for now...
And keep the comm relay safety
margin at fifteen percent!
Ships detected at three o'clock.
High-speed, heavy flotilla.
Receiving a signal from the
Fourth Fleet flagship,
the Senapati...
"Our fleet hereby unites with
the Joint Forces in the effort
to establish peace in
the world as desired by
the Augusta and her
loyal subjects."
Were you trying to ditch me,
old friend...? How rude.
Your reply, sir?
It's about time.
Ships up ahead...!
I count fifty... no... seventy
super-dreadnaughts...
The Third and Fourth Fleets!
There's no true
freedom in this country.
Tied down by old edicts
and outdated traditions.
So where does that lead us...?
To fighting and stealing!
You are still a child.
You cannot understand.
I understand this isn't right...
I want to soar...
through free skies...
No one's going
to stand in my way!
Come back here! Raha!
Perhaps you should
have gone with Sorush
and the Fourth Fleet instead.
No... I believe in
the Premier's cause.
Only he can do what needs
to be done for this world.
All hands, battle stations!
Giant Claudia Unit
acoustics ten miles ahead!
Artillery loading...
Main gun preparing to fire.
The Grand Exile...
All forces, prepare for combat!
Roger!
We are now approaching
the altitude ceiling.
Prepare for battle!
Prepare to fight!
Assemble the floating docks...
Let's give 'em a foothold.
Altitude limit reached.
Commence Boreas Strategy!
And fire!
The enemy's been rendered
virtually blind and deaf!
Let's give that old soldier
a farewell he'll never forget!
Why...? Why won't they stop...?
More death is the
last thing she wants!
Incoming fire! Impact
in three... two... one...
Object approaching...
speed at three hundred knots.
Threat imminent!
What is it?!
The Fourth Fleet's Kumara
and Guha are down!
What's happening out there?!
The Grand Exile is attacking...
...launching
direct strikes using
some kind of
ultra-high-speed objects.
The Grand Exile has them, too.
The Exile defense mechanisms.
Give the Fourth Fleet support!
Enemy fleet approaching
at ten o'clock.
The Grand Exile
is loading artillery.
Ten tons, maybe more!
Alert all ships and
order evasive action, now!
All comm relays are down.
We have no way to communicate!
What? No!
Hey!
Come on... Can't we do anything?
If we go out there now,
we'll just get
ourselves blown to pieces.
The Augusta's flame will
transform this dark world...
We must defend her at all costs.
Not a single ship can be allowed
to approach the Grand Exile.
Artillery loading complete.
Main gun is about to fire!
We must hurry!
What's that sound?
Gimme a casualty report!
Down a third of our forces.
Unusual wind noise from
the Grand Exile's outer hull.
From what I can tell,
the gun and the shielding
surrounding it have
broken off somehow.
What?
It would seem the big ones
are single-use only, then.
Engines to full.
All ships to flank speed.
Engines full.
All ships flank speed!
We're going to
send our intrusion
team through that opening.
We'll launch all
Vanships after we've
successfully breached
the enemy vessel.
First we need to get
inside the Grand Exile...
Then we retrieve
the Augusta as planned.
Grand Exile gun located at one
o'clock is preparing to fire...
Target orientation,
one-hundred-ninety-one degrees!
What is their projected target?!
The Turan royal city, Iglasia.
He's going to
destroy Turan again?!
But that's not
a military base...
Ades immigrants
live there now, too.
It's a message.
"That which is born
of your blue surface."
Replace the combat modules
on all damaged ships!
Incorporate all
the remaining ships
from both the Third
and Fourth Squadrons...
We need to break through!
Change of formation...
Move all heavily damaged
ships to the rear of the fleet.
"May our serenity be
complete and everlasting."
Liliana...
Last Exile.
They used an Exile as a shield.
What's that...?
What's happening out there?
Something's definitely odd.
I need you, Father...
Lily too. I need you to
do something for me...
Please, keep my friends safe.
All ships, charge now!
To Inverted Wedge formation...
Fend off the enemy's charge.
Hello, friends...
I took the liberty of
bringing reinforcements.
Vincent and Wina!
Anatoray backup!
It's about time, Sophia.
Order to all ships from Empress
Sophia of Anatoray Disith...
Support the Joint Forces...!
Run up the banner!
All Joint Forces
ships flank speed now!
Follow the Silvana's lead!
That should give us
some breathing room...
New focus: do whatever we must
to get inside the Grand Exile!
Evade...! Five to starboard.
Move...! Trim-up 15 degrees!
The Silvius must break
through the enemy lines!
All ships: launch as
soon as the hatch opens.
Do not fall behind! Understood?
Output has reached
eighty percent now.
All systems are nominal...
We're all set for takeoff.
Guess this is it, huh?
Well, Birdbrain...
hope you're ready.
Good tailwinds.
Yeah, same to you guys!
Just hold on...
We're on our way, Sara.
Show 'em what we can do...
Go, Fourth Fleet!
Please, Lady Millia...!
Save the Augusta!
Bow-mounted,
long-barrels... Ready guns!
Fire!
All ships, go!
Okay, Sara... we're coming!
Fam... Giselle...
Dyan... Good luck!
So this is the inside
of the Grand Exile.
This all seems...
familiar somehow.
Fam, keep going!
What about you, Captain?
I've missed doing this...
It's such a rush!
Don't get distracted.
Prepare to ram them...
All hands, brace
yourselves for impact.
Just how big is this ship?
We gotta hurry!
Captain Tatiana, Millia, and all
the others are still in danger!
Yeah, just as I thought.
Yes... I agree...
This isn't right at all.
You just wanted to
create a world where
everyone could smile again.
That way!
Hold on!
Enter the pipe at nine o'clock!
What?
That one is our best bet.
It will give us
the shortest route!
Really...? How do you know?
Because it looks like the
Grand Exile has the same
basic structure as the
Federation's Flagship,
the Impetus.
Jet-propelled shells...
Fire... now!
In eight seconds,
take a hard right...
five... four... three...
two... one... mark!
Left turn in six seconds...
four... three...
two... one... mark!
Right in five...
four... three...
two... one... mark!
Whoa!
Heh... It's about time we
got a piece of this action!
All right guys...
Let's show 'em what we got...
Firing!
Go Fam, we'll cover you!
Thanks you guys...
May the wind carry your wings!
Almost there...! Just ahead!
Dyan!
Whoa, this looks... unfinished.
Seems like it was abandoned
during construction...
Unbelievable.
All right then..
Train all guns on
their interior walls!
Draw the tentacles'
attention to us!
That's why I'm here...
Fire!
To unify the world...
to bring lasting peace...
There comes a point
when you must realize
that life is about more
than blindly following orders.
The Premier's
method will undoubtedly
produce the quickest results...
And you think this Exile
is going to fulfill that dream?
It's what the
premier himself wishes...
He issued these instructions...
Please, no more!
No more death!
It's my dream!
And I will chase it!