[in Russian]
Smothered Mate.
Thank goodness...!
I can't believe it!
You're both all right!
I missed you so much...
And you too... All of you!
It's crazy to think about...
This whole time, they
could have destroyed us...
They just looked
the other way...
Like we weren't worth
their attention.
We thought we were
the pride of the sky...
but I guess that
was just a fantasy.
Why us...? What threat are we?
All we want to do is fly.
Oh... I forgot...
Atamora wanted me to pass
a message along to you.
He says our remaining ships
and people are at your disposal,
to help you however
you need going forward.
All right, Atamora!
He wants that? Are you sure?
For what purpose...?
I'm powerless now.
If there's one thing we know,
it's that you're our best
hope in this struggle.
If anyone can do it...
well, you're the one.
Thank you all so much...
No matter what happens,
I will never forget this...
No... Turan will never forget.
Okay, enough with
the formality...
Let's just do our best,
like we always do!
I won't let your
generosity go to waste...
I swear, somehow I will defeat
the Federation...
I'll make them pay... Not just
Luscinia, but Liliana too...
I'll destroy them both!
Uh... don't you think that's
a little much...? Heine?
Uh... Yeah...
First order of business, I need
to borrow several Vespas...
While the Federation's Anshar
is busy undergoing repairs,
I would like to retake it, for
use as my flagship.
Sure, if that's what you want.
Yes, thank you.
Is it me, or has something
about her changed?
She's been like this
for a while now.
I apologize for
the time it took,
but the First Fleet
is here, Premier...
That we were not swift enough
to join the other forces
in battle against Glacies,
I am deeply sorry.
Don't be... You still
have a part to play.
At long last, our goal
is nearing completion.
It has been how long...?
Ten years... Yes?
Yes... You have
supported me well...
and for that I thank you...
Sincerely, I could not have
done it without you...
I am in your debt.
I have lent you my assistance,
but the rest is your doing...
You have led the Federation
well these past years.
Thank you.
How long will it take
to rebuild our forces?
We can make the First
Fleet our primary force
for the time being...
but it will take
roughly one week
to resupply and reequip
the Third Fleet.
The Second and Fourth
can be repaired...
However, they're heavily
damaged from the battle
and require a month to
regain full strength.
Your reconnaissance
seems to indicate
that Anatoray's military power
has been undermined now that the
Silvius is out of the picture.
I think the First and Third
Fleets should have
no trouble dealing with
them on their own.
Impatient as ever, I see.
It is a fault of mine.
I'd hoped they would surrender
after seeing the power we wield.
Unfortunately, it seems they
wish to remain unreasonable.
Yes... we have no choice...
We will attack in one week...
I leave the details to you.
Gloria, Augusta.
And your plans?
I will return in time...
There is a reason I came this
far north... my old friend.
Then you...?
So... The Premier
is going off on his own?
He is... Until he returns,
I am in charge of
the occupation forces
and the Glacien
interim government.
What is the meaning of this...?
Why would he choose
now of all times to leave us?
What could be more important
than our current fight?
It is not our place
to question him...
If Premier Luscinia believes
what he is doing is necessary,
then we must believe it as well.
I don't know the details
of what he plans...
...though I can't help
but remembering
something he once said.
He knew of something that
could usher in a time of peace
such as the world
has never known...
...and obtaining it was more
important than anything else.
This isn't right!
Would you please
calm down, Orang?
All we've fought
for is world peace...
In everything we have done, that
has always been our true goal.
We have shed so much blood...
We have suffered... And still...
that isn't enough for him?
Whatever he's
searching for, it must be vital
to the goal he's
worked for all this time.
Really...?
Then what is his goal?
No... clue... Still...
One thing we can't doubt...
The Premier has
been utterly selfless
in his leadership for
many years now.
The citizens recognize that...
and support him for it.
Yet this is the best we
can do for them?
Now you start doubting...?
We've used the Exile...
Or have you forgotten Turan?
I did not witness the
violence of its descent before.
Ah... and the 'seeing it'
is what unnerved you.
Death is death...
Maybe you end up with your
head displayed on a pike...
...or pulverized by
a barrage of cannon fire...
...or ground into
dust by an Exile.
Does the method matter...?
All casualties of
war end the same.
So...
You would call this justice?
Well... I couldn't say...
But maybe that is because I am
a mere soldier in all of this.
Perhaps he knows more...
perhaps he can see further...
Who are we to
question his vision?
I do know this...
This is a cold land.
Last Exile
Hey, it's her...!
We're with you Princess!
The people of Kartoffel
will never abandon Turan!
Princess!
Princess Millia!
You're looking too thin,
Princess!
I hope you're getting
enough to eat!
So... Princess Millia has taken
a liking to potato
pancakes, huh?
Yep, and on Fam's
birthday she even tried
whipping up a
batch all by herself...!
Can you believe a
princess would do that?
That's impressive for royalty...
Millia's road
will be a long one...
I think she'll need all the
support you can give her.
Oh, hello.
I'm glad you're all right.
Lily, no, how could you?
Please stop this...! Lily!
Hey, Millia.
Hungry?
I'll pass for now.
Okay.
So... Fritz and
the gang are getting
everything prepped
so we can be on our way.
After we get the Anshar back,
maybe we should
go visit Anatoray...
It's supposedly way
off to the east,
so it'll probably
take us a while.
But I bet we could
find out what happened
to the Silvius that way...
We can see how the others
have held up through all this.
What do you think?
I want to continue our
alliance with Anatoray...
We need the strength
of their military forces...
But we don't have time t--
Millia.
The people of Anatoray...
they're more than a military.
I'm sorry...
Oh... no, it's okay...
I just want you to
let other people
share this
burden, that's all.
How can I...? She's my sister.
I'm responsible for Lily.
But obviously Luscinia's
controlling her.
She's under nobody's control...!
It's her... and whatever the
case, I have a job to do...
She's activated
the Exile twice now,
and it's my
responsibility to stop her.
But, still...!
No, it's true...!
Please understand.
This is something
I have to take care of.
So, you're willing
to kill Princess Lily?
I am.
Don't you see that's crazy...?
She's the only sister you have!
Sorry!
Well...
It's looking like they'll be
ready to go by tomorrow morning.
I dunno...
Don't you think it'd be smarter
to hold off for a while...?
I mean, they've been flying
practically non-stop,
haven't they?
Yeah, well...
you've seen Princess Millia.
Do you really think
she'd agree to wait now?
Sorry...! I need
you guys right now!
Giselle!
What's the matter, dear?
This isn't like you at all.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Is it Princess Millia?
Yeah.
Hey, Gigi!
Fam is looking for you.
You sure you
wanna try this again...?
Are you guys just
gluttons for punishment?
Hey...!
Do you wanna get out
here and race instead of us?
Oh... no... I wouldn't
wanna steal your thunder.
Okay, all good here.
I'm ready when you are.
I was born ready!
Well, here we go...!
Three... Two! One! Fly!
Oh! She's at it again.
Fam's always been this way...
It's what she does
when she's feeling upset...
She challenges whoever
she can find to a race.
Better pick up
the pace, Birdbrain...!
Unless eatin' our dust
will cheer you up...!
I'll show you!
Easy... Our engine
is already at its max.
Hey, Gigi... sorry
for dragging you along.
Don't be... I probably
need this as much as you do.
Well, good...! Let's punch it!
Later suckers!
What...?! How is she winning?
Well... she was part of
the Silvius crew for a while...
Makes sense that she's better.
It's not like we haven't been
through a hell of a lot, too...
Let's go!
It's an excellent match.
Kind of like the Grand Race...
I imagine it... just like this.
This is what I want to see.
Fam! Get ready!
Roger!
I want everyone to smile...
No matter what land they're from
I want everyone to
be happy again!
But...
It's just so... beautiful.
We're gonna show
you once and for all!
Heads up!
We lost the lead!
Fritz isn't bad, eh...? He might
hold onto the lead after all.
No way... Fam's got this.
Huh?
That's just her... She makes
people believe... Always.
I'll destroy them both.
I feel so helpless...
What can I do?
Once again, Fam is right.
I don't want to do it.
I don't want to.
Is it really so much to ask?
Just to see people smile?
If there's any
way to avoid it...
Lily...! I don't
want to kill you!
Dammit... Dammit!
Damn it!
What's the matter?
Such red eyes. Look at you!
Look at me...?
What about your eyes?
Yeah, whatever... I'm allowed
to be sad sometimes.
Your turn...
What's with your eyes?
It's nothing... I just got
a little dirt in them.
Right! I musta gotten a
little dirt in mine, too.
You said you were sad!
Am I addressing
Princess Millia of Turan?
Yes... I am Princess Millia.
Excellent...
I come bearing a
message that requires
your immediate
and direct attention.
A message for me?
The official seal
of Augusta Sara!
Wha--? As in
the Federation's ruler?
"Let it hereby be known...
Augusta Sara is deeply troubled
by the repeated acts of violence
perpetrated by Premier Hafez...
and has decided he must be
brought to justice
without delay.
"To that end...
...she would like to
extend an offer of peace,
as well as the promise of
aid to all who have suffered
as a result of Luscina's
reprehensible actions."
"Princess Millia of Turan...
The Augusta humbly
asks for your support in this."
I don't get it.
What's happening?
Well if we're
reading this right,
the Augusta's going to get
rid of Premier Luscinia.
This can't be from her alone.
She's too young.
Someone from within the
Federation helped her...
Someone who wants to
rise against Luscinia.
We've never been to Ades before.
Everyone in the
Federation really
adores the Augusta, right?
Well, that's partially
because she's so young.
I wonder what kind
of place she lives in.
I bet it's a super
swanky royal palace!
That's not how
I've heard it described.
Oooh! I wonder if she'll welcome
us with a fancy banquet!
Just thinking about
it makes me drool.
I'm so excited!
That's enough, you two!
We're not going
there to have fun!