Now passing Saman Lookout...
Speed, one-eighty...
Bearing correction,
five degrees starboard.
Distance to royal city
Iglasia is four hundred.
Roger that.
These are strategic
instructions pertaining
to the defense of the capitol.
It is crucial that you deliver
it to Father personally.
You're telling me to
get off the Lahsas
and continue to
Iglahsia without you?
I won't do it...! I want to
stay beside you and fight.
Millia.
Please. Our father
needs you by his side.
That is your place right now.
But, Lily...
I will meet up with
you in Iglasia.
Promise me you'll be careful.
Take care of her.
You're sure this is
what you wanna do...?
You don't think a Turan pilot
would be a better
choice for this?
I don't believe so.
You two can out-fly anyone in
these skies... Isn't that right?
--Yeah!
Gotta admire how observant
the princess is.
Didn't take her any time to
notice how talented I am.
Are you okay? Feeling scared?
No... I am most
certainly not scared...
I just don't know
how comfortable I am
putting our fate in the
hands of Sky Pirates.
We'll be entering
a jet stream soon...
Please hold onto Fam for safety.
Jet st--? Ahh!
What's going on?!
Fool's mate.
As far as compensating
you for your services...
We are prepared to offer
twenty tons of wheat,
and forty tons of Claudia ore.
Additionally, we will grant your
people the right to trade freely
in Turan territory
for two years.
Sounds fair enough...
In exchange, you have my word
Kartoffel will spare no effort
to assist Turan
in this struggle.
--Princess! Princess!
--Over here! Look!
--Let me have your autograph!
---Woo-hoo! Love you!
I thank you...
Under different circumstances,
this ship would
already belong to you.
Even with her wings clipped,
the Lasas is still
a beautiful vessel.
Indeed.
And don't worry; Kartoffel
will take good care of
any of your soldiers who
were wounded in the battle.
Huh?
Good tailwinds, Princess.
Right... I leave both
my sister and soldiers
in your capable hands.
The Fam Fan Fan is
the obvious choice...
Uh... huh?
You know, the ship you
and your sister gave us.
I'm planning on renaming it just
as soon as this battle's over.
Exiting the jet stream
in fifty seconds.
That's ridiculous. You can't...!
Our flagship already has
a perfectly good name.
Don't go calling
it something stupid!
Pretty rude callin'
someone's name "stupid."
Someone's name...?
Well, yeah... That's
her name. Or, sort of...
Down to ten seconds, Fam.
What do you mean, sort of?!
My name is Fam Fan Fan.
And yours is Giselle Collette.
Three... Two... One. Mark!
Let's go!
So, it's settled...
As of tomorrow, the Lasas
becomes the Fam Fan Fan.
No! I refuse to accept that.
Uh, too bad, 'cause the ship
kinda belongs to me now...
That was my agreement
with Princess Lily.
My sister is a kind,
caring, wonderful woman.
Yeah, I could totally tell
when I met her... And?
And, I can't let you take
advantage of the situation,
and rename the Lasas
without her knowing!
We've received updated
reports from Fort Zwiebel...
According to them,
the Federation fleets have
regrouped over
the Bolur Islands.
They're continuing their
advance on Iglasia.
So, we're looking at six
ship-of-the-line fleets
along with four
siege ship fleets.
Now we got siege
ships involved, too?
And that marker
represents the Impetus.
I also got word of
their progress...
Sounds like they've just
passed Saman Lookout.
Slower than I'd expect.
Their fourth fleet
is amazingly swift,
but otherwise, Federation
ships are rather sluggish.
Their firepower and armor are
nothing to sneeze at, though.
We shall strike the Impetus
with the Lasas herself!
We will pierce the heart of the
enemy with a decisive blow...
It will cripple them...
All we need to focus on is
taking out Premier Hafez.
The other fleets will
crumble quickly enough.
Can you walk?
Of course I can...
I don't need help from you.
Due to heavy fog in
the Belhall region,
the 1502 flight to Madiran
will now be stopping at Huelva.
The Madiran flight is over here!
We need to hurry!
--We were so worried!
--Make way!
This is a private ship.
Has His Majesty still not left?
Princess Millia!
Marianne!
Thank goodness you're all right!
Everything will be fine...
I'm back now, and I'm not
going to let the Federation
lay a hand on Turan.
Right.
Please, don't worry.
My sister has entrusted me with
a way to protect the kingdom.
We will not fall to them.
Millia...
Oh, Father!
You're alive,
I've been so worried.
Yes... and Lily's safe, too.
She is...? Oh, thank goodness.
She says we must use this
to protect the royal city.
Liliana...
Evacuations have begun to try
and save our fair people...
But Millia, you must now
get to safety, as well.
What about you?
My duty is to see this
through to the end.
Then you must let me stay, too!
Even if all our land is taken,
Turan will not fall so long
as it has its ruler...
Dear... Millia. If only one of
us can survive, it must be you.
So this was what Lily had
planned from the beginning.
You girls are Sky Pirates, yes?
We are.
Come.
You have my thanks for bringing
my daughter safely home.
Oh... it was nothin'.
Liliana would not
lightly entrust her sister
to someone else's hands.
You must be very
skilled pilots indeed.
Now I ask... Will you
keep protecting her?
Yes.
Of course.
I hope you will accept that
ring as a small payment...
Take her to the imperial villa
in the east, out of harm's way.
Father, no!
Don't cry, my dear...
You are our only hope,
Millia, please be strong...
The fate of our nation now
lies in your capable hands.
A father... huh.
Why can't they all
just run away together?
Do what...?
The Princesses,
and their father--
they should all try to escape!
If the kingdom survives
but its king dies,
all this is for nothing!
You know I'm right, Gigi.
I'm ready... We can go now.
ETA at Turan,
eighteen hundred hours...
Main Turan forces
have been deployed
to the fore of the royal city.
They'll fight to the death.
King Turan is no fool.
He knows the objective
of this battle.
He knows our goal
is annihilation.
All craft, to
battle stations!
Use all necessary force to
destroy their army and capital.
Today we show our
resolve to the world!
Our enemy will be
watching the skies...
The Federation favors
visual patrols...
And their spotting
technology is bar none.
But if our ruse has worked,
and they believe the Lasas
has sunk into the Grand Lake,
we should be able to
catch them off guard.
If we locate the Impetus
before they spot our approach...
our victory will be assured.
Impetus sighted.
Currently five miles
off Cape Aster,
heading South towards Iglasia.
Instruct all ships:
go to silent running...
Our only target is
Luscinia's command ship...
We must bring down the Impetus!
Last Exile.
Luscinia Hafez is
our sole target!
Destroy him at all cost!
A Turan fleet... Fifteen ships,
including the Lasas.
So then she did survive.
Luscinia...
Full ramming speed!
Destroy the Impetus!
Enemy flagship
approaching from above!
Evade, now!
All right! They've got 'em!
What happened to the Lasas?!
Roughly two hundred miles
to the Eastern villa...
Should take us about four hours.
You think we should stop
by Kartoffel first...?
They're still tending
to the Turan soldiers
who were wounded in battle.
You gotta stay strong,
Princess, like your father said.
You can't reassure your people
with that hopeless
look on your face.
I am well aware of
that, thank you.
'Course you are.
Okay! Let's get going!
Dio?!
They've taken Princess Lily!
They have my sister?!
The Lasas bridge crew
was slaughtered...
My best guess...
whoever took her must've
brought her to the Impetus.
Will you save her?
Please...! We have
to do something!
We have to save my sister...!
You have to take me to
that ship... right now!
Princess Millia?
They're going kill her,
I know it...
I beg you... please
rescue my sister.
She's all I have left.
Gigi! You familiar with the
inner-workings of the Impetus?
We're goin' in.
Roger!
Well...? Can we enter
from the flight deck?
Doubtful. That's where her
defenses are most concentrated.
Our best bet is between
the rotary propellers.
I'll act as a decoy.
Sir! Sky Pirate ships below!
Forget 'em! The only weapons
they have are harpoons.
Time to dive into the Skyfish!
We're going in there?
Seriously?!
Ahh!
Turning right.
No, Fam! Go back!
Claudia ships have five
ventilation shafts ahead...
Enter the pipe at nine o'clock.
Roger that!
Maintain current speed,
then take a hard right in six...
five... four... three...
two... one... now!
Huh...? A main passageway?
Maybe they're doing repair work?
We need to find a map
of the ship somewhere.
Through the lower
deck Claudia tanks
and parametron computation room,
up the main artillery hoist
elevator, and then let's see...
Through the cooling
tower and air ducts.
Can we do it?
Yeah but I think we ought to
keep using the vents...
They should get us there.
Are you okay?
I'm fine... Don't worry about
me. Worry about my sister.
I promise... we will find a
way to rescue Princess Lily.
We've lost sight of
the Sky Pirate ship...
Last seen near the vents.
Send gunners to every exit!
Eliminate them on sight!
Two...! One! Turn now!
So, you must be--!
Luscinia Hafez!
I'm here for my sister...
You will release her at once!
They're coming this way!
Send gunners!
Permission to fire, sir?
Hold...! Silence, men.
Do not fire.
Are you familiar
with the Exiles?
They are detestable ships...
Emigrant vessels from
the cataclysmic days...
They took those who
wished to flee this world
and carried them to the
furthest reaches of the sky.
When the time of
peril had passed,
they returned as if
it was their right...
as if they hadn't turned
their backs and fled.
But there was no place for
them here any longer...
no land for those cowards who
abandoned their home world
at the time of its
greatest suffering.
I did not come here to
listen to a history lecture.
Now, bring out my sister!
You people should
never have returned.
This is not your home.
Liliana!
Millia... you need
to put the gun down.
What are you doing?
Enough, Luscinia... you win...
Turan surrenders to
the Ades Federation.
Don't, Lily...
I ask but one thing...
Let no harm come to my sister.
Unfortunately, surrender
is not an option.
There is only one way
our world can know peace.
The nations of returned
emigrants must fall.
Some must die so
others may live.
That is your true
objective in this...?
You seek only annihilation?!
Have you forgotten
everything...?
Forgotten the sorrow of the
Grand Race? Farahnaz's dream?
I told you to let her go!
"That which is born of your
waters... Your blue surface."
Wha... What's happening to her?
What have you done to my sister?
"United by a single word...
Joined by a single wish."
Lily!
You see... This is my true
objective, Liliana!
"May our serenity
be everlasting."
Fam!
What's going on?
Why are they retreating?
Is the attack over?
What is that?!
A new Federation weapon?
Fire...! Shoot it down!
An Exile...?!
Hold your fire!
You are a loyal man, and have
served me well... I thank you.
No, my liege...
Thank you for making my life
such a fulfilling one.
Very well.
O, Grand Lake, I pray...
Give the people of Turan
and my daughters
your protection through
all that is still to come.
Gigi...! Gigi!
I'm fine.
Where's the princess?
Millia!
Millia...
You know what, Millia?
Gigi's actually a
really good cook.
She's got a big family,
so she's always helping out.
Fam.
Potato pancakes
are her specialty!
They're pancakes
made out of potatoes!
There's not much land here,
so potatoes are about
all we can grow.
Fam, please.
Just wait until you
take a bite of one!
They're nice and warm and
fluffy and they make you feel
like you're being
hugged on the inside!
They'll cheer you
right up, Millia! I promise!