[STUDENT A]
Have you heard yet?
[STUDENT B]
About what?
[STUDENT A] That transfer
student we're getting.
[STUDENT B]
Transfer student?
[RYOICHI]
It's kinda sweet...
This unique scent on the air.
[RYOICHI]
So then...
This is the Earth.
[RYOICHI gasps]
Hey.
[KENJI] It was sunny and
full of cherry blossoms
on the day that I first
met Ryoichi Kyogoku.
[NATSUKI sighs]
[NATSUKI panting]
[KENJI] But, it turned
out that meeting Ryoichi
wasn't the only
event of the morning.
The morning itself
was pretty normal.
The usual breeze,
the usual sunshine.
[KAHORI]
You come by every day, right?
[KENJI]
Huh? Huh?!
[KAHORI] It's so nice that
you take him out for exercise.
Uh, yeah? I kinda have to.
Good boy! Now what's your name?
[giggles]
Uh... K-Kenji.
It's, uh... Kenji Seki.
[KAHORI laughs]
I was asking the dog, Seki.
I already know your name.
We're gonna be in
the same class.
--[SHIRO barks]
--[KAHORI laughs]
Uh... His name's Shiro.
Shiro for "white."
[KAHORI]
Well, hello there, Shiro.
[KENJI] We hadn't even
had our opening ceremony,
and I'd already
spoken to Harukawa
from the Student Council!
This was, without a doubt,
the highlight of my entire year!
Shiro! Nice job!
And today, will be
the greatest--
[NATSUKI]
Nice, you pervert!
What are you doing ogling
Kaho like some pervert?
Go and take that creepy
stare of yours outta here.
--Creepy...
--[KENJI growls]
Stop that! I was
not being creepy!
Mr. Policeman!
[KENJI]
Wha?!
There's a predator on the beach!
[KENJI]
Stop that!
--[NATSUKI] Somebody save me!
--[POLICE] Huh?
--Policeman! Over here!
--Natsuki! Cut it out!
[KENJI]
Ugh!
[groans]
[NATSUKI]
Yep, pervert.
You're-- You're the one who--
[NATSUKI]
And...
[KENJI]
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
That there is my evidence.
[KENJI gasps]
How long...?
[NATSUKI]
The whole time.
[KENJI]
Really?
[NATSUKI]
Really.
And I'm sure Kaho noticed.
Like, it's super obvious.
[KENJI groans]
Please kill me now.
[KENJI] So, the second
event of the morning
was this little tragedy.
Made much, much worse
by the fact that it
was witnessed by
Natsuki Suzuura.
If she ever spread
this around school,
I would be--
[groans]
Your new name is Mr. Open
Zipper from this day on.
--[KENJI gasps]
--[NATSUKI laughs]
[KENJI]
I had been presumptuous
in declaring it the
greatest day of my life.
[laughs nervously]
Yup, that's the guy!
[KENJI]
Seriously?!
[POLICE]
Hey, kid, over here!
[KENJI] Later, I'd realize
that meeting Kyogoku
is what had mattered
most that day.
I didn't have any
clue at the time.
It would still take me
a while to figure out
just how much had
been set in motion then.
[NATSUKI]
Kaho!
--[KAHORI giggles]
--[NATSUKI] Hey!
Saw you at the
beach earlier!
Oh, you were around?
[NATSUKI]
Mm-hm!
The beach is on
my jogging route.
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
So beginning this term,
all cell phones will be
banned from school property.
There'll be some push back,
but we ask that the faculty
does their part enforcing--
[MR. SAITO]
Sorry.
[RYOICHI gasps]
If you just take your seat,
I'll be right with you.
[RYOICHI]
Sure.
[KAHORI]
Oh, I ran into Seki afterward.
[NATSUKI]
Really?
[KAHORI] Yeah, he was
walking little Shiro!
[NATSUKI] You know, he used
to take that dog out at night.
It looks like he's tryna
be an early bird this year.
Kaho? What's wrong?
[KAHORI]
Huh? There's nothing wrong.
[NATSUKI] Oh, please,
do not tell me that boy
was at all
inappropriate with you!
Hey! Come on, I didn't
say anything like that.
[NATSUKI]
So! What then?
What happened? Tell me!
Tell me, tell me, tell me!
[KAHORI]
About what?
--[bicycle rattles]
--[KENJI panting]
[KENJI]
Damn, it's hot out!
[bicycle bell rings]
[STUDENT C]
God, this sucks!
I can't believe they
banned cell phones.
[STUDENT D]
I know, right?
Who's the rule even good
for except the teachers?
--Aw, it's stupid is what it is!
--Yeah, but I kinda get why.
After last year...
[STUDENT E] Ugh, repeating
your second year's
gotta be the worst!
Oh yeah. Wasn't she
in your club?
People have been
talking about her.
[STUDENT E sighs]
I would bail from day one!
[sighs]
[STUDENT C] And you text
in class, too, Akari.
Sure, I'm just saying...
Even the Student Council's
on board with it.
--I do not believe this!
--[STUDENT D laughs]
[KAHORI]
Huh?
[STUDENT C] So, people who don't
understand what a pain this is
get to make up our
minds on our behalf.
Saori, be nice!
Why do we have to suffer
through some dumb rules
made up by people who
can't even relate to us?!
[MR. SAITO] If you can actually
stay focused during class,
then maybe we can re-evaluate
this cause of your suffering.
If that's all right.
Besides, I'm guessing
you're more annoyed
than truly inconvenienced
by this new rule of ours.
[SAORI sighs]
[STUDENT D]
Saori?
[gasps]
I respectfully disagree!
[MR. SAITO] Then, why not
run home between classes
to use your phone?
[SAORI] Huh? What'd be
the point of that?
[MR. SAITO] Saori, do you
actually need your phone
in the middle of class?
Not really, I guess.
[MR. SAITO] Do you need
it during recess then?
Yeah! Of course!
[MR. SAITO] Why's that?
Important business calls?
[SAORI] No, but I have to read
my texts and check twitter!
[MR. SAITO]
And all of that absolutely
needs to happen during recess?
[SAORI]
I guess not...
I didn't text all that
much during school.
[MR. SAITO] Hm, so if it's
not important during school,
then just what's
the problem with
not having your precious
cell phone in my class?
But the rule's so strict!
[MR. SAITO] Lately, many of
you have been distracted
by these phones that you
don't seem to actually need.
So then, what's the harm in
just not bringing them in?
Does this mean Sai agrees with
the whole rest of the faculty?
That's disappointing.
[MR. SAITO]
That's Mr. Saito to you.
And sorry if I can't empathize,
but my generation
didn't have cell phones.
Don't worry, that's it
for personal anecdotes.
Honestly though, just because
the internet and cell phones
are meant for communication,
doesn't mean they
really connect you.
I'm not saying cell
phones are bad,
just that junior high students
might stand to gain
a little bit more
from interacting with
their peers in real life.
And that's why the faculty
feels the way that they do.
[bike rattles]
[footsteps]
[MR. SAITO]
But enough of that.
It's time for the long awaited
arrival of our new student.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KENJI panting]
[KENJI]
Did I... make it?
[STUDENT G]
Yeah, right!
[MR. SAITO] Seki, the bell
rang already, so definitely not!
Aw... dammit!
[sighs]
You idiot.
I bet that you went right to
bed after walking your dog.
Why am I not surprised?
[KENJI]
Ugh, leave me alone, okay?
Then I won't warn
you your fly is down.
[KENJI gasps]
Huh?!
Come on!
[NATSUKI laughs]
Now, you're just being mean!
So now I'm offensive,
Mr. Open Zipper Guy?
[KENJI] Madam Suzuura, would you
kindly never talk about that?
[NATSUKI]
Oh, pardon me?
I didn't catch that.
Ugh, would you just please,
please shut up?
Pretty please?
Pretty please.
[giggles]
[chuckles]
Huh?
They're a lively bunch,
aren't they?
Okay! Now it's really time
to introduce him, isn't it?
Sure.
Go right ahead!
[RYOICHI] Well, I just recently
moved here from Hanamaki.
So I'm still in my old uniform.
My name's Ryoichi Kyogoku,
and it's nice to meet you all.
Uh, hey...
What's up?
The new student...
[RYOICHI]
Huh?
Do you know him or something?
Yeah. I ran into
him this morning.
Really?
[RYOICHI sighs]
[KAHORI sighs]
[chuckles]
[bell chimes]
[SAORI] Hey, Kyogoku!
What's your number?
[RYOICHI]
Hm? My number?
Yeah, for your cell.
[RYOICHI] I've never had
a cell phone, actually.
What? Why not?
I've never needed one.
--[AKARI] Just like Mr. Saito.
--[KAHORI gasps]
[STUDENT F]
Are your parents against them?
[RYOICHI]
It's not that...
[KAHORI]
Hm?
[RYOICHI] I'm able to
get by fine without one.
Is that weird?
[AKARI]
Just a little.
[SAORI sniffles]
But what about text messages?!
[RYOICHI]
I'm fine without them.
Come on, Saori.
It's not like the boy is
holding out on you, all right?
[KAHORI sighs]
[STUDENT D]
He's not giving you his number
because he doesn't have one!
[NATSUKI]
Gotcha!
[BOTH laugh]
Whoops! So what are you doing?
Um... I'm reading this poster.
[NATSUKI]
Uh... About fleas?
[KAHORI]
Sure... Amazing creatures!
--Don't you think so?
[NATSUKI] Kaho! Hey, wait!
[RYOICHI]
A drama festival?
[STUDENT E] Have you
ever done a school play?
[AKARI]
This year, Mr. Saito is gonna
oversee the festival, himself.
[STUDENT F] I really liked
being in Mr. Saito's class
last year.
[RYOICHI]
Oh.
[SAORI]
Kyogoku, have you thought about
joining any clubs yet?
You're so tall! What about
the basketball team?
[KENJI] Huh. That new transfer
student's the mysterious type.
[NATSUKI]
Of course he's mysterious.
Anyone can tell that!
[KENJI]
Really? How?
[NATSUKI]
Handsome guys just are.
[KENJI]
So, what? He's handsome to you?
[NATSUKI] I'm just going off
what the other girls said.
Kyogoku was all
they talked about
when we all got
dressed for P.E. today.
[KENJI]
Huh...
[NATSUKI]
Hey!
[KENJI]
Huh?
No more dirty thoughts, okay?
I... wasn't-- Ahh!
[NATSUKI] ♪Mr. Open Zipper,
Mr. Open Zipper.♪
That's seriously
getting old now!
[sniffles]
So what does mysterious have
to do with handsome anyway?
You know, girls can
be mysterious, too.
[KENJI scoffs]
You kidding me?
[NATSUKI] ♪Mr. Open Zipper,
Mr. Open Zipper.♪
[KENJI]
Well, girls can't all sing.
[JINNO] Not one
student's happy about it.
[KONDO]
The cell phone rule?
[JINNO]
What else?
[KONDO] You outta
hear my class complain.
They think it's way too extreme.
[AMANO] And they're all
pissed at the Council..
...for not consulting the
entire student body to weigh in.
They're saying we're traitors.
[SOGA]
All right, then.
Before we consider a reaction,
I'm wondering how each of us
feels about the
rule to begin with.
Amano, first?
[AMANO] Personally speaking,
I'd say I'm in favor of it.
[SOGA]
And Kondo?
[KONDO]
I agree, too.
[SOGA]
And Harukawa?
[KAHORI]
Yes, I do, too.
It's not like cell
phones are a necessity.
[JINNO sighs]
[SOGA]
And Jinno.
I'm in favor of it
since I've gotta be.
That girl from the big cell
phone incident last year
was a classmate
of mine, after all.
Right, Yuriko Yamagiwa is
in my class this semester.
[SOGA] Cell phones
may be convenient,
but if using them harms even
one of our own classmates,
then there isn't any choice.
They need to be
banned altogether.
That does seem like
the safest answer.
I think people are
really just upset
'cause they didn't get
a say in the matter.
[SOGA chuckles]
It's strange, isn't it?
Individually, anybody would
share our opinion.
But as a group, there's nothing
but outrage in the air.
There sure is.
I wonder if it's even
possible for us all
to choose our own
opinions to begin with.
Or if it's just... up to
whatever goes around in the air.
Now don't be silly.
Every one of us gets to
make up our own minds.
[piano music plays]
[JINNO] I wish things
would be that simple.
[SOGA]
Of course, they are.
What do you mean?
[JINNO] Like, what if
someone causes you
to feel a certain
way about them?
[JINNO] Did you choose
that feeling yourself?
Or, do we get influenced by
something in between us
instead of what's
only inside our heads?
[piano music continues]
[gasps]
Huh?
[sighs]
[KAHORI gasps]
[KAHORI pants]
[RYOICHI]
Harukawa, right?
[KAHORI whimpers]
[train whistles]
[RYOICHI] The room was free,
so I thought I'd practice.
Should I... have asked first?
[KAHORI]
No, don't worry.
I-It's fine!
Anybody here's allowed to
use one as long as it's free.
[RYOICHI]
All right.
[KAHORI]
Thank you.
[RYOICHI] So did you
come for practice also?
[KAHORI]
Uh, yeah!
[RYOICHI]
Oh, you're diligent.
[KAHORI]
Oh, no.
I just don't have
a piano of my own.
Really?
[KAHORI]
That was "Clair de Lune"?
[RYOICHI]
Mm?
[KAHORI]
Debussy's "Clair de Lune."
[RYOICHI]
Yeah. It means "moonlight."
I like...
[KAHORI gasps]
[RYOICHI]
...the moon.
[KAHORI laughs nervously]
Is that strange?
Oh! No, not strange!
It really isn't
strange at all!
[laughs]
That's good.
[RYOICHI]
Thanks.
Kyogoku likes...
[KAHORI]
...the moon.
[FAMILIAR]
I'm sorry to interrupt
while you're clearly relaxing.
Know that your abilities
were not meant to be...
...squandered in this era.
[RYOICHI] I could say the
same of you, showing up.
[FAMILIAR] I'm to pass your
report onto Professor Kyogoku.
I would hope you haven't
lost sight of your mission.
[FAMILIAR]
This is the moon.
It has a yellowish
hue in this era.
It's unsettling.
[RYOICHI]
Even so, it's beautiful.
[FAMILIAR sighs]
[RYOICHI chuckles]
[RYOICHI] "...for aught
that I could ever read,
Could ever hear
by tale or history,
The course of true love
never did run smooth..."
[RYOICHI] "Or, if there
were a sympathy in choice,
War, death, or sickness
did lay siege to it,
[RYOICHI]
Making it momentary as a sound,
Swift as a shadow,
short as any dream..."
Hey, uh... the next few
lines are Lysander's, too.
[RYOICHI] I'm sorry, but what's
the point in doing this?
[NATSUKI gasps]
The point?
[RYOICHI]
Yeah.
[KENJI] Hmm... Uh, I don't think
staging plays is about a point.
[RYOICHI]
Is it a rule?
It isn't. It's sort of about
something else, I guess.
[RYOICHI]
So... What then?
[KENJI]
Mm... Yeah, why are--
[groans]
[MR. SAITO]
Sounds like you're quite
the young philosopher, Kyogoku.
[NATSUKI]
Hm?
Do you know why we do this?
Well, I'll try to answer.
The playwright of
"A Midsummer Night's Dream"
had said that when
it comes to acting,
its purpose is to "hold,
as 'twere, the mirror
up to nature;
to show virtue her own feature."
[giggles]
[MR. SAITO]
Virtue is well and good,
but we invented mirrors
to see ourselves.
So along with grand ideas,
I'd say acting could
also show us ourselves.
[RYOICHI]
That seems like a stretch.
--[NATSUKI] Hmph!
--[MR. SAITO chuckles]
Theatre'll let you get
out of your own head
for a little while,
and try to understand a
totally different person.
Try to understand?
[MR. SAITO] Right! Maybe when
you experience that,
you'll finally be able to answer
your question for yourself.
They call that...
being in the moment.
Mr. Saito, way to dance
around simple questions.
[MR. SAITO chuckles]
Okay, a bit too grandiose.
But I do hope you guys
are able to enjoy this.
You're all here to learn!
And acting can offer you
kids as much life experience
as you're willing to let it.
[KAHORI]
Is Mr. Saito always so chatty?
[NATSUKI] Yeah. Me and
Kenji had him last year,
and the guy hasn't
changed a bit.
[KAHORI]
Really?
[KENJI]
Sai... is pretty laid-back.
Except about being called "Sai."
That, he hates.
[KAHORI chuckles] Oh, it really
bothers him that much?
[KENJI]
Not enough to stop anyone.
[GROUP laughs]
[KAHORI] Kyogoku, what made
you so curious earlier?
[NATSUKI]
Oh yeah, what's up?
[RYOICHI]
Hm...
I was just wondering
how it's useful to repeat
a bunch of words to each other
that none of us actually mean.
[NATSUKI] Well... that's just
what you do in school.
[RYOICHI]
I mean, they're not our words.
[NATSUKI]
Yeah, but...
I know it might seem
kind of pointless,
but it's not like anyone
is able to go around,
sharing exactly what we
mean in every little detail.
But everyone can share
the meaning of a play.
All right. I think I get it now.
[KENJI]
Huh...?
[groans]
[NATSUKI] Wow! You can't
even pretend you understand.
I... guess not. Oh!
[KAHORI giggles]
Looks like you can share what
you mean without words, too.
It would seem so.
And I guess I don't
understand anything!
[RYOICHI]
You know, Seki,
you might be a
little more intuitive
than you give
yourself credit for.
--[KENJI] Huh?
--[RYOICHI] Am I wrong?
Ha, ha! Are you kidding?
He's no mind reader!
[laughs]
[KENJI]
Oh...
[RYOICHI]
Mm.
[RYOICHI] Wow! The view from
up here is really amazing!
[NATSUKI]
I know, right?
Come on, you guys!
[RYOICHI]
A kite, like the bird?
[KAHORI]
Yeah, I'm not even kidding!
One swooped right down
and stole my lunch
when I was just a little kid.
[RYOICHI chuckles] That sounds
like a very rude bird.
[RYOICHI, KAHORI laugh]
It's nice and calm up here.
You think so?
That's nice.
I was hoping you'd like it.
[KENJI]
Hmph.
[NATSUKI]
Oops!
You better watch it or a
bird'll eat your food!
[KENJI]
Ugh!
[NATSUKI] You know, she'll just
think you're a pervert
if you keep gawking
at her like that.
Aw, crap! I was staring?
Yep, a whole lot.
Extremely perverted.
[KAHORI]
Hey, what's up?
[KENJI gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Nothing! We're good!
[KENJI sighs]
[NATSUKI]
Hmph.
[NATSUKI] Geez...
you're that hung up on her?
[KENJI chuckles]
So you're the mind reader.
[NATSUKI] Please, I don't need
to be when it comes to you.
[KENJI sighs]
[NATSUKI huffs] You're being way
too obvious, just get over it!
[KENJI]
I can't!
[NATSUKI]
Sure you can!
[KENJI]
Natsuki...
Don't act like you could
understand something like this.
[gasps, grunts]
[KENJI]
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
Why would you say that?
[KENJI]
Huh?
What the hell would
you know anyway?!
[KENJI gasps]
Natsuki?!
[NATSUKI grunts]
[KENJI groans]
[panting]
[groans]
Huh?
[gasps]
[sniffs, cries]
[KENJI]
Huh?
Natsuki?
[MAGICIAN]
And what you drew on the card...
...was none other than this!
Whoa! You got it! That's it!
But how did you do it?
[MAGICIAN] I heard the
answer within your heart.
[TV MAN]
Wow!
[applause]
Telepathy, it's just
a matter of science.
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
Oh...
[KENJI] That stuff's
obviously just an act.
Yeah, I suppose that
it would have to be.
[KENJI] Life would be a lot
easier if I could read minds.
Boy, can I not.
You know, psychic powers
are like cell phones.
When you're old enough,
you'll find that you don't
even really need 'em.
[KENJI] What's that gotta
do with being old?
Oh, I do admit that
holding onto mine
does make certain
things easier for me.
Grandpa Koji! You've got
psychic powers?!
No... I was talking
about my cell phone.
But why the sudden
interest in powers of mind?
[KENJI]
Mm... Hm...
Haven't you ever wondered
just what the hell
other people are
really thinking?
'Cause I sure do.
Huh?
Now you always know
exactly how to help.
Thanks a lot.
Guess I needed that.
[KOJI]
Hm.
[KENJI'S MOTHER]
Kenji!
Come help your
father in the kitchen!
[KENJI]
Coming!
[clack]
[pumping]
[NATSUKI groans]
[clack]
[NATSUKI gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Dammit, that's enough-- Ah!
[gasps]
You okay?
Ow!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
What the hell do
you want from me?!
I tried calling. You wouldn't
answer your cell--
Not an answer!
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry for earlier.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
[KENJI]
Sorry.
I'm sorry that I said
you couldn't understand.
I need you to know...
The truth is...
...that I...
I actually...
I really do like,
uh... Harukawa.
[gasps]
[KENJI] So, I really want
some advice from a girl
on how I should, you know--
[NATSUKI growls]
Goddamn moron!
[grunts, coughs]
[KENJI]
What just happened?
[GIRL gasping, panting]
You can't do this.
[gasps]
[GIRL screams]
[GIRL crying]
[GIRL sobs]
Why? Why bother saving me?
[RYOICHI]
Why?
I didn't do anything.
You never really meant to jump
in the first place, did you?
Don't talk to me
like you know me!
[RYOICHI]
You're Yuriko Yamagiwa,
in your second year
of middle school...
...for the second time.
You think that no one ever
understands how you feel,
so you figure you
may as well jump.
But you never actually
wanted to die.
What the hell's with you?!
You've never even met me before!
Yes, that's right. I didn't
need to. After all...
...I can just understand you.
It's so clear, the voice
inside your heart.
[sniffles, laughs]
You do want to live,
more than most people.
And you're right, no one
else understands--
[YURIKO]
Just shut up!
[sobs]
[FAMILIAR]
Ryoichi...
[RYOICHI]
Yeah, I know.
This girl could be
a perfect candidate.
[gasps]
[RYOICHI]
Do you want to understand...
...what others really think?
Wait, what are you--
[RYOICHI]
You already have the potential,
and that is why I was able to
hear the sound of inner voice.
[YURIKO] What is this?!
Tell me what's happening!
[YURIKO whimpers]
Come with me, Yuriko.
And I promise...
I promise that no one
can ever lie to you.
[KAHORI'S MOTHER]
Kaho, you still there?
[KAHORI gasps]
Sorry... I'm here!
[KAHORI]
Sure, don't work too late, Mom.
Bye.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[overlapping voices]
[NATSUKI]
What? I'm trying to sleep.
Whenever I'm pissed off,
I just wanna stay in bed.
[overlapping voices]
[NATSUKI]
Will you just stop bothering me?
What the hell do you want?
[KENJI] Natsu, they're
so great, aren't they?
[NATSUKI] I like you, Ken,
I like you... a whole lot, Ken.
[gasps]
They're so cool!
Don't cha think?
I think we'll see 'em
even better over there!
Come on!
[NATSUKI yelps]
[footsteps]
[NATSUKI]
Hey, Ken, tell me.
[KENJI]
Hm?
[NATSUKI] What do
you wanna be some day
when you're all grown up?
I'm gonna stay and run the inn
because everybody
loves staying there.
That's great!
That means that you and me
will stay neighbors forever.
[KENJI] Don't you want to move
away to Tokyo or something?
[NATSUKI] I like you
more than anybody, Ken.
[KENJI]
What?
[NATSUKI]
I said, I really like you a lot.
[KENJI]
Hm?
[NATSUKI] I like you
the best, Ken! I mean it!
What's that?
I like you! A lot! A lot!
[gasps]
[KENJI]
Huh?!
I said that--
[alarm rings]
I like you the very,
very best, Ken!
I like you so much!
I love you!
[NATSUKI]
That dream again...
[NATSUKI] How long's it been...
since I had that one?
[NATSUKI'S MOTHER]
Natsuki?
Are you up yet?
[NATSUKI] I should've
learned back then that
no matter what, the two of us
could only ever be so
close to each other.
We've lived next door to
each other our whole lives.
Same preschool, same elementary
school, same junior high.
We were always classmates.
Even our lockers were
right next to each other.
I'm his next door
neighbor and...
...that's all I am to him.
That's how it's been and...
...that's how
it'll stay... always.
Always...
[KENJI]
Huh? Oh, Natsuki--
[KENJI gasps]
[NATSUKI cries]
[NATSUKI]
If I could just...
[NATSUKI giggles]
[NATSUKI]...make myself
feel nothing for him.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[NATSUKI]
Hm?
You guys going in?
[STUDENTS]
Um...
Then quit blocking the door.
[NATSUKI]
Hey, Yamagiwa, what's up?
[YURIKO]
Good morning, Suzuura.
[NATSUKI] Oh! I didn't
realize you knew everyone's
names already.
[YURIKO]
From the seating chart.
[RYOICHI]
Good morning.
[NATSUKI]
Uh, morning!
[YURIKO chuckles]
[NATSUKI]
Uh...
[KAHORI]
Yuriko seems pretty mellow now,
like nothing even happened.
[NATSUKI]
Yeah, but what's changed?
Why start coming to school now?
Good for her, though.
[KAHORI]
You were worried about her?
[NATSUKI]
I guess I was.
But, I'm also kind of nuts
about never missing any school.
[KAHORI] So you've still
got perfect attendance?
[NATSUKI laughs]
Sure do!
[KAHORI]
Miss World Champion.
Any potential threats
to your record?
[NATSUKI]
I never get sick.
[KAHORI]
So not even lovesick, then?
[laughs]
No way, not a chance!
[KAHORI]
You never know.
--Sometimes it just... happens.
--[NATSUKI] Not to me.
And if it did, I think
that I'd just spend
even more time here at school,
to keep an eye on him.
[KAHORI] Knowing you,
yeah, I guess you would.
So... How 'bout
that transfer student?
[KAHORI gasps]
[laughs]
Oh, come on, Kaho!
You know I'm gonna make you tell
me everything no matter what!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[KENJI]
Uh...
This is great.
Seki, you're already here!
[KENJI]
Uh... Huh?!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Wait, why are you here?
Huh? Wait! Hold on!
Why are you questioning me?!
Like, how am I supposed
to respond to that?!
Uh! Sorry, I must've just, uh--
[YURIKO giggles]
Sorry, my mistake.
Please, go ahead and ignore me.
Huh...?
Photographing the sky?
Specifically, the clouds.
The clouds?
Yeah, these are ones that
I think look like stuff.
[RYOICHI]
Oh, so what's this one?
Uh, oh, this?
It's a burger!
Huh? Okay... What's this?
It's a cheeseburger.
[laughs]
[KENJI]
Huh?
[RYOICHI]
Oh, come on!
--I can't believe you!
--Hey, just take a closer look!
This part totally looks
like melted cheese!
--[stomach rumbles]
--[BOTH] Huh?
You wanna get something to eat?
[KENJI]
Mm-hm.
[platform beeps]
[NATSUKI sighs] I guess love
at first sight is real, huh?
[KAHORI] Hey, I'm really
sorry for making you
listen to me go on
and on like this.
[NATSUKI] No, I'm glad
that you're sharing.
You're so proper and you
hold things in sometimes.
[KAHORI]
I'm trying to keep it together,
but... I'm not that proper.
It's okay if you are, Kaho.
That transfer student's
one lucky boy.
He's great at the piano, too.
[NATSUKI]
And talented, too.
[nervous chuckle]
[KAHORI] It's so weird to
feel all this out of nowhere,
and for someone I just met.
[NATSUKI] Aw... I wouldn't
stress out about it.
No one's ever said that love
makes any sort of sense.
[KAHORI]
I guess not.
[NATSUKI] That's the one thing
about love that I do know.
[NATSUKI] So, exactly when are
you spilling your guts to him?
[KAHORI] Um, I was
planning to just... not?
[NATSUKI] What? Why?! You've
gotta be straight with that boy.
And while you still
have a shot with him.
[KAHORI sighs]
Losing my shot sounds easier.
[elevator dings]
[BOTH]
Wow!
[KAHORI]
The view is amazing today!
I-I don't ever think it's
been so pretty from up here.
I think this might be
the most beautiful sunset
that I've ever seen
in my whole life.
[chuckles]
[KAHORI]
Natsuki...
[NATSUKI]
Yeah?
[KAHORI] You really don't
have a crush on anyone?
[NATSUKI]
Nope, not me.
[KAHORI]
Come on... What about Seki?
[NATSUKI]
Geez, Kaho...
The boy has been my next
door neighbor like, forever.
And how could I ever like
somebody as dense as him?
[KAHORI] Oh... So that's
really how you feel?
[gasps]
Natsuki?
I already told you.
We're just friends,
nothing more, nothing less.
He and I are simply
neighbors, that's all.
And if you don't
believe me, just ask him.
He would say the
exact same thing.
[KENJI] You really
are mysterious, you know?
[RYOICHI]
Why's that?
[KENJI] You've never
eaten a single hamburger!
[RYOICHI]
And that's mysterious?
[KENJI] Yeah! Are your
parents strict about food?
No, it's nothing like that.
[RYOICHI]
It's nice...
[KENJI]
Hm? Ah...
[KENJI] Hey, there's something
I keep meaning to ask you about.
[RYOICHI]
What's that?
[KENJI] What did you mean by,
"So then, this is the Earth"?
[RYOICHI]
Have you told anyone about that?
[KENJI]
No? I shouldn't?
[RYOICHI] People...
might think that I'm strange.
[KENJI]
A little too late for that!
[RYOICHI chuckles]
But weren't you wearing
your headphones back then?
Uh... I guess so.
[RYOICHI] So you're a
mind reader, after all.
I must be.
[RYOICHI]
You'd heard right.
[KENJI]
Huh?
But I wasn't speaking
out loud then.
I know how this sounds, but I
do think you're a psychic.
It's hard to tell
when you're joking.
[RYOICHI]
I'm being serious.
So you're what? An alien?
[RYOICHI]
Don't be silly.
I'm from the future.
[laughing]
And now we've got a
psychic and a time traveler
eating hamburgers together,
as they whimsically
admire the sunset.
It would seem so.
[RYOICHI] Couldn't have
said it better myself.
[MAGICIAN]
Now I'll reach into the future
and grab the food
you most desire.
[TV MAN]
What?
[MAGICIAN]
3... 2... 1... Open!
--[TV MAN] Wow!
--From the future, huh?
[MAGICIAN] You wanted
a hamburger, didn't you?
[TV MAN]
Yeah, I did!
[MAGICIAN] Time warp,
it's just a matter of science.
[FAMILIAR]
Ryoichi...
You're spending your time
sampling this era's food?!
Don't get any more
involved than needed,
especially if you're aware
that this Seki boy is--
[RYOICHI]
He'd only get in our way.
Wouldn't he?
Even so, my dad went
and picked his era.
Just for revenge.
[FAMILIAR]
It's not my place to speculate
on the Professor's
personal feelings.
[RYOICHI]
Is conflict unavoidable?
[FAMILIAR] The boy could
indeed pose a threat.
I can say nothing
further on the matter.
Now, let's move forward
with the mission.
You've already found several
that have latent abilities,
so let us allow the
people of this era
to adequately handle
their own affairs.
[NATSUKI exhales]
[grunts]
[footsteps]
[KAHORI] You're jogging
a lot more lately.
[NATSUKI]
Yeah, I guess.
I'm aiming for a
high school in Tokyo
that's got a good track team.
[KAHORI] I'm sure you'll
get a great recommendation.
[NATSUKI]
Heh, we'll see.
I've just been thinking it
might be nice to get away.
[KAHORI] You've got
practice after school?
[NATSUKI]
Yep.
You staying for
a Council meeting?
[KAHORI]
About the cell phone ban.
Something to do with...
disciplinary actions
since not everyone's
complying yet.
[NATSUKI] If you're
practicing piano later,
maybe I'll see you after.
[KAHORI]
Yeah, sure!
I'll wait up for you.
So those two have been
hanging out a whole lot lately.
They have?
[NATSUKI sighs]
Oh crap... Hey,
I didn't mean it like that.
[coughs]
Well, it's none of my business.
[NATSUKI]
Of course not.
[KAHORI] Hey, let's keep
this quiet at school.
[MR. SAITO]
What part of speech is this?
[STUDENT D]
I know, it's spoken!
[AKARI]
Geez, Toyama...
[TOYAMA]
I'm not wrong!
It's a prefix.
[MR. SAITO]
Yes! That's correct!
[sighs]
[MR. SAITO] And what
comes after a prefix is?
[TOYAMA]
Also spoken!
[KENJI]
Are you still mad at me?
I'm sorry I shot
you with an acorn!
I mean it! I really
am sorry, okay?
Did it hurt that much?
[KENJI pants]
[KENJI grunting]
Wah!
Yes, it hurt a lot.
Because you hurt me right here!
Huh?
I hurt... your boob?
[growls]
Ah! Uh, oh, oh! Wai-Wait!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
You... Agh!
[NATSUKI]
Moron!
[KENJI]
N-N-Natsuki!
[grunts]
[NATSUKI] Come on...
You're never late, Kaho.
[sighs]
Huh?
[KAHORI humming]
[NATSUKI grunts]
[NATSUKI]
Hm?
[JINNO] Hey, have you
seen the Council president?
[KAHORI]
Uh... No, I haven't.
I just figured that
Soga was absent today.
[JINNO]
Huh. Weird.
I was sure I'd seen
her in the morning.
[KAHORI] Well, she wasn't at
our Council meeting, so...
...maybe she left early?
[JINNO]
Hm.
[NATSUKI gasps]
[KENJI]
Uh... Huh?
[NATSUKI screams]
[gasps]
What... the hell is all this?
[YURIKO]
This... is a test.
A test that proves whether
we are ready for the future.
Soga has proven herself.
Huh?
What are you talking about--
[YURIKO] And unfortunately,
you haven't, Suzuura.
As hard as I try, I hear
nothing inside your heart.
[NATSUKI]
Uh...
[FAMILIAR]
Yamagiwa, please.
[NATSUKI gasps]
[FAMILIAR] You've already
said far too much.
Our mission is too important
to jeopardize with
idle conversation.
Okay, did that
thing just talk?!
[YURIKO] I really was hoping
that you could be one of us.
You're such a
nice person, Suzuura.
It's just such a damn shame.
[NATSUKI yelps]
That hurts!
Ow!
[NATSUKI whimpers]
[NATSUKI screams]
Help me, Kenji! Help me!
Stop this, now.
[NATSUKI yelps, screams]
[YURIKO]
Mm. Hm?
[thud]
[NATSUKI]
Ow... What the hell?!
[NATSUKI cries]
[FAMILIAR]
Ryoichi...
[NATSUKI groans]
That really hurt.
[RYOICHI]
Are you okay?
[gasps]
Huh?
[RYOICHI] It's important that
you don't talk about this.
All right?
[NATSUKI]
I don't even know what this is.
And what are you?!
[RYOICHI] You're saying
I don't look human?
[NATSUKI]
I mean, you look like one, but--
[RYOICHI]
Ssh. Somebody is coming.
You should go now, quickly.
[KAHORI humming]
[FAMILIAR]
Hmm... Very well, then.
For now, it's enough that the
Student Council president
is one of us. I'm certain
this will aid our progress.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[KAHORI humming]
Hm?
[sighs]
--[RYOICHI] Hey! Harukawa!
--[KAHORI gasps]
I'm glad I found you.
[RYOICHI] I... sort of...
borrowed these without asking.
Thanks.
Oh, are you going to practice
"Clair de Lune" also?
[KAHORI]
Um, yeah!
I thought I'd try it out.
Then I'd like to hear it.
Someday.
[KAHORI]
Mm-hm.
What the hell is
taking Natsuki so long?!
[KAHORI sighs, giggles]
[KAHORI] I don't remember all
that much about my father.
He was a fisherman.
One night, years ago,
there was a terrible storm,
and he was pulled under while
trying to rescue one
of his shipmates.
My mother was always
afraid of the sea after that.
She worries so much
when I'm out swimming.
I think that's why coming
here is the only time
I can feel just a
little bit... rebellious.
I can't believe that my father
had ever lived in
fear of the water.
So, I won't either.
[KAHORI] It's like...
I can feel him here.
[KAHORI] It's almost like
I'm speaking with him.
[KENJI]
Whoa!
[KAHORI gasps]
Shiro!
[KENJI]
Ah! I'm sorry about him!
Good boy!
Now, how old are you, Shiro?
He's pretty old...
A teenager, actually.
Oh! That's pretty old for a dog!
Yeah, he's been around
as long as I remember.
Well, he certainly
doesn't show his age.
Yeah. I wonder how he does it.
Uh, by the way, Harukawa...
Have you seen Natsuki lately?
[KAHORI]
Mm-mm.
I haven't seen her
at school for days.
Oh...
[KAHORI]
You heard anything?
No... She won't answer her cell.
Really? Same with me.
I'm a little worried.
[KENJI]
Hm.
[KAHORI] Guess her perfect
attendance is shot.
She... told you
about her record?
[KAHORI]
Yeah... She was proud of it.
I guess that leaves
the honor to me!
[KAHORI]
You've never missed a day?
Tardiness... is another matter.
[KAHORI]
Oh...
[gasps]
Uh... Harukawa?
Yeah?
[KENJI]
Are you thinking of...
...maybe dating... anyone?
[KAHORI]
Huh...?
[bike rattles]
[KENJI groans]
[cat meows]
[SOGA] The policy bans not
only the use of cell phones,
but their possession on
school grounds as well.
Despite this, many students
continue to bring them in.
They aren't respecting the rule.
So obviously,
the penalty for breaking it
needs to be much more severe.
I feel, the Student
Council should propose...
[JINNO]
...suspension?!
That's pretty harsh, isn't it?!
Not for disobeying
school policy.
I get that students are
supposed to obey the rules,
but what gives us the right
to hand out that
kind of punishment?!
[AMANO] I think we
could actually do this.
Article 10, Supplement
number 2 says:
"The Student Council may propose
new school policy measures
when deemed necessary.
Such policies are effective
upon student body approval."
[JINNO]
Even so, they'd never agree.
[SOGA] It also says that
in cases of emergency,
approval by the student
body may be circumvented.
[JINNO] But our advisor
would never okay that!
[SOGA] Mr. Yamada happens
to be out on sick leave
until further notice.
[KAHORI]
Huh?!
[AMANO] Then approval from a
faculty advisor isn't needed.
This doesn't make sense!
Mr. Yamada was
just fine yesterday!
So then what the hell
happened to him?!
We should all put
this to a vote.
[gasps]
W-Wait! We've barely discussed--
All in favor, raise your hand.
[JINNO] There's no way a
majority of us would agree to--
[KAHORI gasps]
[KONDO cries]
[JINNO]
The hell...?
[AMANO] It looks like
we have the majority.
What's the matter?
[JINNO]
Hm...
The policy has been approved
by the Student Council.
[crying continues]
[KAHORI gasps]
What's going on with them?!
[JINNO]
No clue!
[KAHORI] I mean, why are
the rest of the Council
acting like completely different
people all of a sudden?!
I know just as much as you do!
[gasps]
I'm sorry...
It's just that...
it seems like...
Like it isn't just
the Student Council
who have been acting
so unusual lately.
So many opinions are
changing all of a sudden.
One student after another.
Constantly, now.
You know, it's not just Mr.
Yamada who's suddenly taken off.
A bunch of students
are out also.
--Twenty-three, so far.
--What?
And it's making me nervous,
especially since not one of them
is even returning my calls.
I think people were
glued to their phones
'cause they were
afraid of being isolated.
School can feel pretty
lonely sometimes.
But the ones who've changed
don't seem to feel
that way anymore.
Almost like they can just--
--[KAHORI gasps]
--[JINNO] Sorry.
You'd just think
that I'm the one
who's turned into
someone else.
Please, tell me what you think!
It's like the ones
who've changed can...
...speak without words.
Huh?
[JINNO]
I know telepathy sounds crazy,
but isn't that how
it seems to you?
[KAHORI]
Um...
Maybe we should check in on
Mr. Yamada after school today.
Don't you think so?
[JINNO] Yeah, I'm starting to
get worried about him now.
I'll run home and grab my
cell phone before we meet up.
What's your number?
[KAHORI]
Actually, I...
[JINNO]
Hm?
[KAHORI] I kind of... uh...
don't have a cell phone.
[phone ringing]
[KENJI] Goddammit, Natsuki!
Just answer your phone!
At least take your pillow back!
[YURIKO]
Are you waiting for someone?
[KAHORI]
Hm? Yeah, I am.
[YURIKO]
Then, would it be all right
if I waited out here with you?
Oh, sure! Don't even
worry about it!
All right.
Thanks, Harukawa.
[YURIKO]
You know...
I think that we'd be better off
without cell phones altogether.
[KAHORI]
Hm?
[YURIKO]
They can cause so much trouble.
They can poison the air
between you and other people.
They're flawed...
if you think about it.
[KAHORI]
Cell phones you mean?
[YURIKO]
Yeah. It's pretty ridiculous.
These little devices trick you
into believing that
you're never alone,
that you're actually
connected with other people...
...when all you're really doing
is avoiding the entire world.
[KAHORI]
Huh. Mm-hm.
[YURIKO]
All this... when there's already
a flawless communication
with each other.
[YURIKO]
I wanted to warn you, Harukawa.
It's only fair.
[KAHORI]
Warn me?
[YURIKO]
Yes.
Stonewalling the
Council like this
isn't going to
help out anybody.
Not in the end.
[KAHORI]
Huh?
[YURIKO]
Jinno, right? The Council VP?
It's a shame that he couldn't
make your little date today.
[gasps]
What did you do to him?
I hear he's moved.
[gasps]
[YURIKO] Everyone is better
off without cell phones
because it's only without them
that people will look for
what we've already found.
Honestly, wouldn't
you love to know
what people are really thinking?
What they feel,
not what they say.
[YURIKO] Just think of
how lonely it can be
when you can't understand
how someone feels,
or when you're not able to make
someone else understand you.
[KAHORI] Yamagiwa, what are
you saying we should do?
[YURIKO]
We should be reborn,
if we're able to.
Then we should gain
the ability to survive
in the world that's coming.
He told us about it himself.
[KAHORI]
Who did?
You aren't talking about--
[YURIKO]
Do you want to try?
Maybe you'll belong.
[KAHORI]
Try what?
I-I don't get it.
[YURIKO]
Just look at these soap bubbles.
--[KAHORI] The soap bubbles?
--[KENJI growls]
[YURIKO]
Yeah, look.
Each and every one of them is
a whole world unto themselves.
Hm. Take a look,
and you can see them,
all of these different
worlds on the inside.
And each of these
worlds, unfortunately,
are isolated from one another.
I think that's sounds lonely.
All that we want...
...is for them to be connected,
so that they
aren't alone anymore.
[KAHORI gasps]
[KAHORI]
But they popped.
[YURIKO]
Some will pop.
But some will join.
So there's a test,
to learn which one you are.
[KAHORI]
What?
[KAHORI grunts]
Ow!
[screams]
[KAHORI pants]
[yelps, groans]
[gasps]
[KENJI]
Hey! Harukawa!
[KAHORI panting]
[KENJI panting]
Harukawa! What's wrong?!
[KENJI]
Are you all right, Harukawa?
[grunts]
[KAHORI]
Are you all right, Seki?
--[YURIKO gasps]
--[KENJI] Come on, let's go.
[KAHORI yelps] Seki! Hold on!
I can stand up on my own!
[KENJI]
Uh, sorry!
[KAHORI]
It's fine.
[BOTH panting]
Harukawa!
[SOGA]
Hm...
And we're really sure
that boy has our ability?
He didn't respond to
my inner voice at all.
[YURIKO] Still though,
but he did come here for her.
There's something there...
[SOGA] Maybe Harukawa
reached out to him.
[FAMILIAR]
No, it wasn't her.
He's one of us, but his
full power is sealed.
And I'm fairly certain
as to who did it,
and for what reason.
[gate rattles]
[KENJI] Huh? Sorry,
I was... holding your hand.
[KENJI]
Huh? Ssh! Ssh!
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
Hm?
Oh! Well, hello, you two!
--[KENJI] Ssh! Grandpa, ssh!
--[KENJI'S GRANDPA] Huh?
If it's all right with you,
I think we should
talk more inside.
My room is right at the
top of the stairs, okay?
[KENJI] Oh, I'll get
something to drink--
[crash]
[KENJI]
Ow!
--Come on, come on. Iced tea...
--[clanging]
[KENJI]
Ow! That still hurts!
[rattling]
[KAHORI]
Hm?
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
[KAHORI gasping]
--[NATSUKI] Huh...?
--[KAHORI whimpers]
[gasps]
No! No! Uh...
--I... I'm sorry to intrude.
--[NATSUKI] This isn't what
it looks like, I swear!
Please, K-Kaho!
[KENJI'S SISTER sighs]
[NATSUKI]
Just wait a second, will you?!
Oh my god! You had me startled!
[sighs]
I wasn't expecting
that either...
[KENJI]
Natsuki, you shouldn't climb in
from the roof like that.
It's too dangerous.
[NATSUKI]
Dangerous?!
You nearly took me out
with a freakin' acorn!
[KENJI]
And you... broke your leg
making that climb
when we were little!
[NATSUKI]
That was you, genius!
[KAHORI chuckles]
[KENJI]
Oh... Was it?
Yes! It was!
We were talking on the
string phone and you--
--[KAHORI laughs]
--[NATSUKI] Huh?
[KAHORI] This room feels
like a whole other world
compared to that mess earlier.
I still don't know just
what to make of it all.
Are you feeling any better now?
Yeah, thanks.
I'm not scared anymore.
Scared of what?
Did that transfer student try
something with you, too--
[gasps]
[KENJI]
Huh...?
What did Kyogoku do to you?
Nevermind, it's nothing.
[KENJI]
It's not nothing.
This is the reason you've
been skipping school, isn't it?
[NATSUKI]
I said, it's nothing!
[KAHORI]
I knew it!
[KENJI gasps]
Kyogoku... I knew he had
something to do with...
...w-whatever's been
happening at school.
[KAHORI]
Natsuki, please...
I-I wanna understand
whatever it is
that he's trying to
do to all of us.
[KENJI]
Uh...
Please tell me, Natsuki.
What is he doing?
[NATSUKI whimpers]
[RYOICHI chuckles]
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
Huh...
[KENJI]
But of course!
So, the mystery unfolds.
[KAHORI]
Hm?
[KENJI]
Hm...
So this means--
[groans]
[KENJI] I haven't said
anything dumb yet!
[NATSUKI]
No, but you were about to!
I read your mind, and it told
me that you're a big moron!
[KENJI] I thought they said
you didn't have any...
...super powers or whatever.
[NATSUKI] Yet I can still
tell that you're a moron.
Ooh! How 'bout that?
[giggles]
[NATSUKI]
It's getting late.
I really should start
heading home.
Are you sure it's safe to
go out because you can--
You are not going to make
her stay in your bedroom!
Thank you,
but I'll be just fine.
I'm glad you're okay, Natsuki.
Well, I'll walk you home.
Uh... Me too!
Huh? What, in your pajamas?
Five minutes!
Gimme five minutes!
[KENJI] We've recently talked
about you not doing that!
And you forgot
your pillow again!
[NATSUKI]
Ta-da!
[sighs]
[NATSUKI] I'm glad I
finally talked to you guys.
I really need to
vent more often.
[KENJI] What? You're like
always venting.
[NATSUKI]
I am not!
Don't you pay any attention?
[KENJI]
Fine, then vent more.
All right, if you say so.
But I don't want to
be held responsible
for any future venting.
[KENJI]
Huh?
Hey, Natsuki...
[NATSUKI]
Hm?
[KENJI]
Will you come back to school?
I have no idea how
Kyogoku and the others
are trying to change
things for everyone.
I'd rather that stuff
just stays normal.
And... what's most normal
is us staying friends, right?
[NATSUKI]
Please don't say that to me.
[KENJI]
Huh?
Just don't say that to me!
Natsuki...?
Sorry!
I was just worried is all.
[NATSUKI]
Moron...
[KENJI]
Huh?
[NATSUKI] Come on,
when're you gonna tell me
how Kaho turned you down?
W-What are you talking about?!
Where's this coming from?
[NATSUKI]
Answer me.
And I'll come back to school.
[KENJI]
Uh...
[KENJI groans]
Okay, fine!
If you're gonna be a baby...
[KAHORI sighs]
[KAHORI]
Mm...
[KENJI grunts]
[KENJI]
Hm?
Huh?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Hey, are you all right, Seki?
[NATSUKI laughs]
[KAHORI]
Uh... Seki?
[laughing continues]
[NATSUKI]
Mr. Open Zipper returns!
[KENJI] Now you've gotta
come back to school, okay?
[KENJI] Bring your phone with
you if you're still worried.
I'm gonna bring in mine,
too, all right?
[sighs]
[gasps]
N-Natsuki, what are you--
[giggles]
There, I vented.
You moron.
[KENJI gasps]
[NATSUKI]
I do understand, Kenji...
Liking someone who
likes someone else,
knowing that they just don't
understand how you feel...
...and wanting to know
exactly what they think...
...because you like them...
...and you just can't help it...
...and it feels so awful...
[NATSUKI sobs]
I get it.
I get it better than
anyone else does!
So don't ever...
Don't ever say... that I can't
understand how all of it feels!
[MR. SAITO]
Wait, not even teachers
can bring in their phones?
[YURIKO]
Correct, it's school policy.
So what? The teachers would
get suspended, too, then?
--It's only fair, sir.
--[MR. SAITO] Huh?
[VICE PRINCIPAL] Mr. Saito,
a quick moment, please?
[MR. SAITO]
Uh...
Mr. Vice Principal? What's the--
[VICE PRINCIPAL] Just a moment,
and in private, Mr. Saito.
[KAHORI yelps, laughs]
[KAHORI]
And morning, Natsuki.
[AMANO]
I think each offender needs
the penalty to be
clearly explained.
[YURIKO]
I'm disappointed to hear that
you've ignored
my warning, Harukawa.
[KAHORI gasps]
[YURIKO]
We had held back.
Because he really does seem
to like both you and Seki.
Though I can't see why
that should interfere.
[KAHORI] What did you
do to Jinno and Kondo?
[YURIKO]
Aren't they both absent?
That's why we've decided to
help out on the Student Council.
[KAHORI gasps]
[gasps]
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[gasps]
[YURIKO] I thought you
were smart enough to
try helping us in
whatever way you're able.
So many who don't share our
abilities want to cooperate.
Like the Vice Principal...
He's been more than
understanding with our cause.
[KAHORI sighs]
[YURIKO] That's why the Council
has enacted so many policies
to make this school a
better place for everyone.
--[KAHORI grunts]
--[door slams]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[bike rattling]
[KENJI]
Huh?
Whoa... They took your shoes?
[sniffles]
[KENJI grunts]
[thud]
[KENJI]
Ouch...
Natsuki...?
Natsuki, people can see us.
[NATSUKI cries]
[KENJI] Uh...
[KENJI]
Natsuki?
Get off... We can't climb
up the stairs on my bike.
[NATSUKI whimpers]
Hey, uh, also...
I can feel your...
...boobs against my back.
[gasps]
[KENJI groans]
[NATSUKI]
You creep.
[KENJI]
Fine, whatever.
[NATSUKI]
When you already like Kaho...
[KENJI]
Fine. Whatever.
[NATSUKI] No one is safe
from your creepiness.
[KENJI scoffs]
Gimme a break.
Nobody's safe from you either.
[NATSUKI]
Sorry...
[KENJI]
Put these on.
--Your feet are all scuffed up.
--[NATSUKI gasps]
[KENJI] I guess it was
a crappy first day back.
Are you comin' tomorrow?
Are you coming?
Yeah, I'm gonna keep
going like normal.
[NATSUKI]
Then I will, too.
[piano music]
[KAHORI sighs]
[RYOICHI]
Harukawa...
--[KAHORI gasps]
--Please, don't get involved.
I'd have thought that my
friends had scared you away.
Why even worry about me?
[RYOICHI chuckles]
[RYOICHI] Because it only
takes a single person
to get everybody
else in an uproar.
[KAHORI]
There's something that I needed
to ask you about, all right?
Can you understand everyone?
No, not exactly.
For one, I can't even imagine
just what would make
you come and see me.
[KAHORI] Because I don't
have the ability that you do.
No... you don't.
[RYOICHI]
In the future...
Everybody has been forced to
leave the entire Earth behind.
[KAHORI]
What?
[RYOICHI] We'd spent
too long living in a way
that the planet just
wasn't able to endure.
We'd made the Earth...
uninhabitable.
So, we took refuge on the moon.
Look, up there is my real home.
I can't get over how
strange it feels.
I never thought
I'd have a chance
to look up at the moon
from down on the Earth.
Things happen so fast...
...without any warning.
The only ship to
survive was the one
that had already left the Earth.
Then we learned that it
would take a thousand years
for the Earth to
become livable again.
We didn't have the technology
or the resources
to survive that long.
What remained of us...
were doomed.
We can never return... ever.
[RYOICHI] But as time went on...
there were certain children
who began to
show certain abilities.
[KAHORI]
And those were psychics?
[RYOICHI] Yeah, some would
decide to put it that way.
[RYOICHI]
Those same people would say that
we'd never taken full
advantage of the brain.
And faced with extinction,
it made sense for
latent abilities to appear.
At least, that's what
some believed.
[RYOICHI] But no one
really knows for sure.
Even so, in my era, it's the
only ray of hope we have left.
[KAHORI]
It is?
[RYOICHI]
Yeah.
I don't think anyone
could accept
just sitting around
and waiting for the end.
I think we needed hope
to keep on living.
[NATSUKI]
Uh... Hey!
[RYOICHI] The ability seems to
manifest around the age of 14.
Maybe that's because that's when
we start feeling doubt,
and confusion, and shame
in our relationships
with others.
[NATSUKI, KENJI chattering]
[RYOICHI]
Maybe that's what triggers it?
Some say this ability
comes as a defense...
...to prevent conflict.
So, my mission is
to awaken those
with latent
abilities in this era,
as many as possible.
If what they say is true,
maybe we can prevent
that disaster.
And if I fail,
I'll take all those
that I've awakened
back to my era.
[gasps]
[RYOICHI] After all,
there aren't very many people
who are left in my
time to begin with.
And fewer still
who have the ability.
I won't let anyone get
in the way... No one.
--Not even you, Harukawa.
--[gasps]
[RYOICHI]
And not Seki.
Not anyone.
[RYOICHI] If real life were
"A Midsummer Night's Dream,"
I guess that I would be Puck.
I came to cast my magic onto
the humans of this world.
[KAHORI]
Why are you telling me this?
[KAHORI sniffles]
[RYOICHI sighs]
[KAHORI] What am--
What am I supposed to do?
[KAHORI cries]
[gasps]
[RYOICHI]
I think that maybe...
...fairies can fall
in love with humans.
Do you know of any plays
where that happens?
[KAHORI gasps]
[RYOICHI]
I wonder...
...if maybe I've gone and
put a magic spell on myself.
[KAHORI sobs]
[RYOICHI] Puck seems like
a trickster, after all.
[MAGICIAN]
I'm gonna count down from three.
After that, you will reawaken
with no memory of
what you've seen.
Yet you will feel as refreshed,
as alert, as ever before.
Do you understand?
3... 2... 1... Now!
[KAHORI crying]
[KAHORI] If this were
a magic spell, then...
...I honestly wish that
it would never be broken.
[RYOICHI] My mother was
born here, in this era.
I don't have any memory of her.
They tell me that she died
not long after I was born.
We don't keep pictures.
My father thinks it's worthless
to dwell on the past.
He only ever looks
to the future.
Even so, a few of my
mother's personal keepsakes
happened to get left behind.
Looking at them and trying
to form an image of her
was a secret hobby of mine,
back when I was still little.
[AKARI panting]
Kaho, come with me!
[KAHORI]
Huh?
[AKARI]
Natsuki is in trouble!
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Hey! What are you doing
rummaging around in my locker?
[STUDENT H]
Natsuki Suzuura,
you are suspended
from this campus,
effective immediately,
for a period of ten days.
A second offense will be met
with a 30-day suspension,
and a third offense,
a period of 90--
--[NATSUKI] Give that.
--Hey! What are you doing?!
[STUDENT J]
Hey, stop that!
[NATSUKI]
Give it back!
[thud]
[panting]
[STUDENTS, NATSUKI yelling]
Yeah, all right!
[STUDENT K]
Okay, let's go!
[KENJI yawns]
[STUDENTS, NATSUKI yelling]
[gasps]
[RYOICHI]
Are you sure?
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
Huh?
Releasing Seki's full potential
is just what my dad wants.
[grunts]
[KENJI'S GRANDPA laughs]
Your old man's still got
big ideas, doesn't he?
Okay, go on, boy!
Go on, find your master. Go!
[KENJI grunts]
[KENJI'S GRANDPA] However Kenji
uses his ability isn't up to me.
Not to me or you.
Please relate that
to your father.
He prefers to leave the
past in the past, doesn't he?
[RYOICHI chuckles]
[NATSUKI] Why ban cell
phones in the first place?
I'm coming to school tomorrow.
You got that?
[STUDENTS murmur]
[NATSUKI]
I promised someone.
I'm sorry, but I
don't quite understand
just what it is
you're saying now.
I guess you wouldn't if that
beautiful telepathy of yours
doesn't work on someone like me.
While you're at it,
why not also ban the rest
of us from even talking?
Or listening?
Just what is your point?
[NATSUKI]
Why even ask?
You just want to prop me up
here and pass judgement.
So you can read minds.
You think that makes you better?
You're a bunch of
telepathic voyeurs!
How is a connect real
if we're not motivated
by wanting to say something
or wanting to know--
Don't call us voyeurs!
That's out of line!
If you don't have the guts to
just tell somebody how you feel
then how can they
ever really know?!
And how could you
ever know how they feel
when neither of you are
brave enough to speak up?!
Your problem isn't cell phones.
It's that all of
you are cowards!
[STUDENT M] All of this is
necessary for our future!
[NATSUKI] I don't care
about the goddamn future!
All of us are still trying
to get through today!
That attitude means that
you're the coward here, not us!
It's our duty to fight for--
You're all the ones...
who aren't taking a risk.
[YURIKO]
Huh?
[STUDENTS groan]
[BOTH gasp]
[SOGA groans]
[NATSUKI gasps]
[STUDENTS scream]
Ugh, cut me a break. I just
came from the pool, all right?
[NATSUKI chuckles]
Anyway, if you're collecting
cell phones, then...
Here's mine.
[BOTH gasp]
[NATSUKI groans]
[KENJI]
Go right ahead.
It's all yours.
[STUDENT M whimpers]
--[YURIKO] Huh?
--[STUDENTS gasp]
[RYOICHI] What kind of
person was my mother?
[KENJI'S GRANDPA] Can't you just
read my mind if you're curious?
[RYOICHI] I want to hear it...
in your own words.
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
All right, then.
She was a lovely person.
You take after her.
[RYOICHI]
So I've heard.
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
She was always a woman
of very strong convictions.
And to tell the truth,
I always did have just a
little bit of a crush on her.
I really did wish
that she could've
lived happily in your time.
Do you think she was happy?
Before the end?
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
I was actually hoping that
you'd be the one to tell me.
[NATSUKI panting]
Please don't!
Please don't leave, Ken!
[KENJI gasps]
[ALL gasp, scream]
[KENJI screams]
[RYOICHI]
I really should get going now.
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
Right.
What'll you do in the end?
Well, what do you mean?
[KENJI'S GRANDPA]
One half of you will always be
from this era, here.
So then you couldn't just stay?
Make it your home?
[KENJI sighs]
I can only guess that
people are happiest
living in the era that they
were actually born into.
And I'm assuming that you feel
the exact same way as me, right?
I suppose so...
[KENJI'S GRANDPS chuckles]
It was a silly question,
wasn't it?
[NATSUKI]
Uh...
Huh?
[KENJI chuckles]
[NATSUKI sighs]
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
No way am I touching your phone!
[AMANO groans]
[NATSUKI]
Where will you even keep it?!
[KENJI]
Where do you think?
This swimsuit is all
I've got right now.
[NATSUKI] Then I'm
definitely holding mine!
[KENJI] All right...
What's the big deal?
Your swimsuit is not
a pocket, you freak show!
[laughs]
[BOTH]
Huh?
Like I said, you really
are a psychic, huh?
[KENJI chuckles]
I guess you were right.
[RYOICHI]
Then let's finish this.
We decide how
this ends, don't we?
[NATSUKI gasps]
Oh! Uh, hey, Kyogoku!
[RYOICHI]
Hm?
[KENJI]
Tomorrow's Saturday.
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
[RYOICHI]
Okay...?
Then let's all go to the beach!
[NATSUKI]
Huh?!
[RYOICHI]
Huh...?
[BOTH gasp]
[RYOICHI]
What...?
[WEATHERMAN] The typhoon
that developed on the 4th
continues to punish
the Ogasawara Islands,
now southeast to Chichijima
and moving northeast
at about 200km/hr,
causing strong wind as well as
a drop in absolute pressure.
[NATSUKI] So you really won't
admit this was a bust, huh?
[KENJI]
Hm? Why?
[NATSUKI]
Because the weather
has extremely different
plans from you today.
[KENJI]
But it's summertime!
[NATSUKI]
You're missing the point!
[KAHORI laughs]
It is summer.
[sighs]
Fine, then I'm the bad guy here,
not the damn typhoon.
Don't worry, it's gonna
let up eventually.
Sure, the weather maybe,
but Kenji will be
as stubborn as ever.
[KAHORI] Oh, hey!
I brought the scripts with me.
[NATSUKI gasps]
For... For the school play?!
[RYOICHI]
Great, we should practice.
--[NATSUKI] Right now?!
--[KENJI] Yeah! Nice!
[KAHORI]
I brought some lunch.
Should we eat before or after?
[NATSUKI] So all of us are
ignoring the typhoon then?
Lunch! Let's eat first!
And Suzuura made yours herself.
--[NATSUKI] Uh...
--[KENJI] Oh... Really?
[RYOICHI] Come on,
Seki, don't be rude.
Then I'll try not to pass out...
[NATSUKI]
My food's not the reason
you'll lose consciousness.
Uh... Maybe I shouldn't have--
Hey! Let's all eat together!
[RYOICHI, KENJI gasp]
[KAHORI screams]
[NATSUKI]
It can't be that ba--
[NATSUKI groans]
[KAHORI screaming]
[KENJI] Sorry...
I always make you worry.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
Who are you?
Is Ken gonna--
That's me, there.
And I guess I died back then.
Huh?
[KENJI] But, you slipped
back in time and changed it.
You got hurt in my place.
And it used up all
of your ability.
When something's changed,
then something else has got
to change to balance it out.
[chuckles]
[NATSUKI]
Uh...
Well, all right, take care then.
[NATSUKI]
But... where are you going?
Wait! Wait, Kenji!
[panting]
Don't leave!
Kenji, you promised!
We were always--
We were... always going
to be neighbors! Always!
[sobs]
[NATSUKI]
You liar.
Please don't go!
[NATSUKI]
Kenji...
You promised me!
[NATSUKI]
Kenji...
You told me yourself!
You said... You said
we'll always be neighbors.
[NATSUKI]
Moron.
Don't leave me!
[NATSUKI]
Kenji, you're a...
Don't go!
[NATSUKI]
...moron.
Moron.
[groans]
[KAHORI]
It let up.
[NATSUKI]
Was I... talking in my sleep?
So, I guess you know.
[KAHORI] I've already known for
a pretty long time, actually.
[NATSUKI]
Since when?
[KAHORI] You always
had perfect attendance
just so you could be
close to Seki, didn't you?
I always thought that
was kind of sweet.
[NATSUKI sobs]
But Kenji likes you,
Kaho, not me!
[KAHORI]
Mm...
[NATSUKI]
It's not fair!
I liked him before
he liked you...
[NATSUKI]
...always.
I always liked him... always.
It's not fair...
[NATSUKI sobs]
[KENJI] Okay, so your dad
used to know my grandpa?
[RYOICHI chuckles]
They weren't exactly friends.
Back when my father
traveled to this era,
your grandfather had
stood against him.
[KENJI] Why didn't he
just come with you?
It's only possible to
make one round-trip.
Any more wears out your heart.
[KENJI]
Hm...
So then how come I can feel
his presence sometimes?
Oh, really?
I can't think of why you'd--
[KENJI yells]
[BOTH laugh]
[RYOICHI]
Hey! I'll get you back!
[laughing continues]
[RYOICHI] You know,
I think I do like plays now.
[KENJI]
Yeah?
It's really nice to be
able to talk like this.
[KENJI chuckles]
Talking is like a performance?
It is... if I'm not able
to read your mind.
Your ability is so much
stronger than mine, by far.
[KENJI grunts]
[RYOICHI]
It's like the sun and the moon.
One light is stronger
than the other.
Even though the moon is
still up there in the sky
all throughout the day,
its light will never
shine past the sun.
[KENJI]
Hm.
Hey! What's taking you?!
[NATSUKI giggles]
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Guys! This is really scary!
I'm freaking out right now!
[NATSUKI giggling]
[KENJI]
Ow...!
[NATSUKI]
Here we go!
Guys, get a little
close together, okay?
[ALL laugh]
[RYOICHI]
So this is summertime.
[KAHORI] Oh, so you don't
have different seasons?
[RYOICHI]
No.
In "A Midsummer Night's Dream,"
they all wake up and leave
behind everything that happened,
like they only
dreamed it, right?
[KAHORI]
Uh, yeah, I guess so.
[RYOICHI]
Magic sounds like hypnosis.
Although...
[KAHORI]
Hm?
What happens if you're
put under a spell
and then you end
up falling in love?
[KAHORI]
Huh?
[RYOICHI] If you do fall in
love while you're under a spell,
then does your
love just disappear
as soon as you wake up?
Can love...
really just go away...
...when a spell is lifted?
[KAHORI gasps]
Huh?
[RYOICHI] Well, I'm going
back to the moon... Home.
Going back? When?!
[RYOICHI]
Tonight... I think.
Then you'll probably...
just forget all about me.
Like in the play, right?
[gasps]
[RYOICHI]
Look, this is already filled up.
It is?
[RYOICHI]
Mm-hm.
Filled with all
the time I had...
...with all the months
I've been here,
away from home.
[gasps]
[RYOICHI]
Goodbye.
You'll play "Clair
de Lune" so well.
I wish I could hear it.
[KENJI]
Puck is a real prankster,
but kind of a
lovable one, you know?
[NATSUKI]
Huh? What are you talking about?
[KENJI] Maybe he's
serious in his own way.
Yeah, but that doesn't
make pranks okay.
Well, we don't know
what's really in his head.
Who knows what
magic people think.
[KAHORI sighs]
[KAHORI gasps]
[RYOICHI grunts]
[KAHORI]
Please don't go!
[RYOICHI]
I'm sorry, but I have to.
[KAHORI]
But... I like you so much.
[RYOICHI gasps]
[KAHORI]
Really, I do!
[RYOICHI hisses, sighs]
[KAHORI] And I know that
I could never forget you.
So, if you really
do have to leave--
Please, just don't...
[KAHORI] So if you--
If you have to leave, then--
[RYOICHI]
Please don't!
[sobbing]
[gasps]
[KAHORI]
Then I'll--
[gasps]
[KAHORI]
Then I'll go with you.
[KENJI sighs]
Let's go.
[NATSUKI]
Go where?
[KENJI]
Get on! I was just thinking.
Without you around,
htere'd be nothing else
that could ground me
right here to this time.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
What's that?
I won't repeat myself.
[NATSUKI]
No, wait. What do you mean?!
[KENJI grunting]
Just come on!
[NATSUKI]
Explain yourself! Jerk.
[KAHORI crying]
[RYOICHI]
Sorry...
[KAHORI]
Huh?
[RYOICHI] You know, my mother,
she was from this era.
When she left it
for another one,
I think that she was
always so lonely.
[KAHORI gasps]
[RYOICHI]
Goodbye...
Hey!
[NATSUKI]
Uh?
[RYOICHI grunts]
[KENJI]
Are you alone?
[RYOICHI]
Yeah.
[KENJI]
That's good.
[RYOICHI gasps]
[NATSUKI gasps, yelps]
[KENJI] Well, I figured that
I should come and see you off!
But once you're home--
I'll have to break-- Ah!
I understand, but I really
can't allow you to do that.
[KENJI grunting]
[KENJI yelps]
[gasps]
[KENJI screams]
Wait, Kyogoku! We can't do this!
If I fight you,
you could get erased!
It's fine; I'd accept
anything for our mission.
[KENJI gasps]
Huh?
[gasps, pants]
[gasps]
[KENJI grunts]
[FAMILIAR]
Ryoichi, erase them both!
Take their ability!
Then we can change the future.
Humankind will survive!
[RYOICHI]
And what happens then?
[FAMILIAR]
What?!
[RYOICHI] Listen...
we'll never change a past
that doesn't have any future.
Enough of this.
[FAMILIAR]
You fool! Your logic is absurd!
But I'm right.
You know it, and you've
always known.
Right, Dad?!
[FAMILIAR]
Huh?
[RYOICHI]
After all, you were never able
to return Mom to
this era, were you?
[RYOICHI]
So... that just left me...
[KENJI gasps]
[RYOICHI] ...one who
doesn't belong... anywhere.
[KENJI gasps]
[KENJI shouts]
[FAMILIAR]
No!
Why? Why does the Earth...
Why does it reject
our mission again?!
[RYOICHI sighs]
[RYOICHI]
It looks like... snow.
Wait...
I don't think I've
ever seen snow before.
Oh, right.
It must be from one of those
stories Mother told me...
...back when I was
just a little kid.
[grunts]
[RYOICHI]
Huh?
Wait, Seki!
[KENJI]
You knew this would happen
if you used up your
power before leaving.
Seki, get back!
Or you'll be erased also!
[KENJI]
But Kyogoku,
Even though it's not possible
for you to just read my mind...
...you're still able
to hold onto my hand.
[RYOICHI]
Huh...?
[KENJI]
Isn't that enough?
[KENJI] I can tell that
your hand is warm.
And I can tell
that you're close.
[RYOICHI sighs]
[KENJI]
So, isn't that enough?
[NATSUKI giggles]
[BOTH laugh]
[NATSUKI gasps]
Kenji!
[KENJI, RYOICHI panting]
[NATSUKI]
What?
[RYOICHI]
Why are you... doing this...?
[KENJI] I told you...
that I came to see you off.
[RYOICHI] I'm not able to
exist in this time anymore.
[RYOICHI]
And now, I can't go home.
[KENJI]
Then I'll bring you home.
[RYOICHI]
I'll be erased, no matter what.
[KENJI] I can at least
manage a one-way trip.
[RYOICHI]
That's ridiculous.
You'd only be stranded.
Look, Kyogoku...
There's no one who
doesn't belong anywhere.
[KENJI] The reason that
you're still here right now
is because there are people
who want you to be here.
It's the same for
you as it is for me.
And maybe... for everyone.
[RYOICHI gasps]
[KENJI chuckles]
[RYOICHI sighs]
Maybe... you're right.
[KENJI]
Uh... Sorry, Natsuki.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
[KENJI]
I'll be right back. Okay?
From where?
[KENJI]
Wait for me, all right?
You... You want me
to just wait for you?
[chuckles]
[RYOICHI]
I think...
If I was born in this era...
...we could've been...
[KENJI chuckles]
Oh, quit it.
[KENJI]
Me and you are already friends,
just the way things
are right now.
Time and space wouldn't
change things.
Nothing would.
[NATSUKI yelps, screams]
[gasps]
[NATSUKI grunts]
No! Kenji, wait!
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Uh...
--[KENJI'S GRANDPA groans]
--[KENJI'S SISTER gasps]
Kenji...?
[gasps]
What...? Why am I...?
[NATSUKI]
I said Kenji...
Who is that?
[STUDENT A]
Have you heard yet?
[STUDENT B]
About what?
[STUDENT A] That transfer
student we're getting.
[STUDENT B]
Transfer student?
[phone rings]
[KAHORI]
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
Uh-mm.
I don't know this number.
[ringing continues]
[NATSUKI gasping]
[KENJI] Come on! Will you please
just answer your cell already?
[KAHORI gasps]
Aw, man... That is so weird.
Giving you this phone
call was supposed to
make you remember me again.
[KAHORI gasps]
[NATSUKI sobs]
[NATSUKI]
Moron...
[sobbing continues]
[KENJI]
Natsuki?
[NATSUKI]
Moron!
--[KENJI groans]
--[NATSUKI cries]
[KENJI chuckles]
I'm back now.
[NATSUKI]
You moron...