There's been a direct
hit in Sector 13!
There are also pressure
leaks in Sector 15,
but the damage is minimal.
Well, I guess that's it.
We can't last much longer.
All ships retreat!
But that's impossible!
The enemy is blocking our
path in every direction!
There's no way they'll
come after us.
Unless, of course,
they're completely stupid,
in which case it'll
be a different story!
Squadron space-time bubble,
complete the maneuver!
[ALL CREW]
Roger!
[ LASHKAU CREW B]
All ships! Follow the Lashkau!
[COMM. OFFICER]
The enemy's coming after us!
Distance, 10 sheskedrel.
Space-time fusion!
Two more enemy ships
at 170 degrees!
Looks like the
enemy is stupid!
Oh! Can they really
hate me that much?
Do what you can
to break through!
[grunts]
The Doubilge has exploded.
[SPOOR grunts]
What have I gone and done?
Did I misjudge the
right time to retreat?
[COMM. OFFICER] The enemy fleet
is moving towards Lobnas Gate!
And there's a detachment
force headed our way.
Do you think they're
leaving that route open
to give us a chance to escape?
[SPOOR sighs]
[SPOOR]
You could be right...
[KUFADIS] I don't believe it!
Is she actually thankful?!
[GABORT]
What's the situation?
[ DARKSES OFFICER D]
Checking now...
We have a response!
[DARKSES OFFICER C] The enemy
fleet's passing through
the Lobnas Gate!
Looks like we didn't make it.
What should we do now?
[LAFIEL] We have no other
choice but to go through.
All ships activate their
space-time bubble generators!
All ships prepare space-time
bubble generators... Activate!
[ DARKSES OFFICER D]
Space-time bubble activated!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
The enemy's right behind us!
Okay, here they come!
Prepare for battle!
The laser cannon is ready!
Let's catch up with
the transport ships
and get out of here!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Enemy ships confirmed ahead!
[LAFIEL]
Ignore them and keep moving!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C] Enemy ships
approaching at 45 degrees!
Three more ships
starboard at 90 degrees!
How come they're not attacking?
Maybe this is our lucky day.
Then again, they probably
haven't received any orders
about what to do with us yet.
More enemy ships crossing
our flight path ahead!
We can do it!
If they shoot now, they'll
fire straight at each other!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Ten seconds until we pass
through the Lobnas Gate!
Eight... Seven...
Six... Five... Four...
Three... Two... One...
Passing through!
[ DARKSES OFFICER B] We've
passed through the Lobnas Gate.
All space-time bubbles,
go to maximum speed!
[GABORT]
Get us out of here,
and don't let the
enemy fuse with us!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Roger!
[GABORT] Confirm the position
of the other three ships.
[SOBAASH]
Second Aviator Ekuryua!
What's the current
enemy position?
[EKURYUA]
We're completely surrounded!
Hm?
Deputy Captain, We've received
a signal to regroup.
It's from the Lashkau .
Got it. In that case,
we'd better rendezvous
with Admiral Spoor.
Well, at least the First Fleet
managed to get out of this okay.
[EKURYUA]
Maybe not.
[SAMSON]
I don't believe it.
Is this really all that's
left of the First Fleet?
[GABORT]
There were 33 patrol ships
participating in the battle.
Twenty-six have been
completely destroyed.
Four suffered major damage,
and three,
including the Lashkau ,
managed to escape
with only minor damage.
[LAFIEL grunts] I thought I was
prepared for this sort of thing,
but when so many have died,
it's still hard to deal with.
Their deaths were pointless.
How can anyone say otherwise?
If this is the sort of thing
Her Majesty, the Empress,
has to deal with everyday, I
don't know if I could handle it.
Perhaps I'm not fit to
be a military officer.
What do you mean
you're not worthy?
Have some faith
in yourself, Lafiel.
[LAFIEL] Father... Hm...
I need to be strong.
I think we've discovered the
reason why the enemy ships
didn't attack us back there.
We figure they were nothing
more than supply squadrons.
They wouldn't have had much
firepower at their disposal.
Well that's a relief,
because that makes two of us.
I know they were
only supply ships,
but if we'd been forced
into a combat situation,
we still might
not have survived.
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Yup, we sure were lucky.
We've got confirmation on
the position of the Luise .
All right then, let's exit
space-time fusion
and get ourselves
out of this hell-hole
just as soon as we can!
[LAFIEL] Everyone's going to
blame me for this. I mean...
I know it was my decision that
we got involved in this mess
in the first place...
...but to be honest, I'm more
concerned about the life of the
one person we left behind
than the thousands of lives
lost in battle today.
[LAFIEL]
Jinto...
But what about the enemy?
I don't know! I guess
they'll probably...
I think we can win this.
[KAHYUL] Thanks to the
First Fleet's efforts,
we now know that their strength
is less than half of ours.
Plus we know that
they'll need time
to replenish their supplies.
[KAHYUL] They're taking a risk
by leaving the Lobnas System
via the Salks Gate. But that's
because they don't know that
we're here waiting for them.
They're probably only heading
towards the Salks System
as a last resort.
[TRIFE]
So what's the plan?
[KAHYUL]
We have two options.
Firstly, we can cut them off
before they go through the Gate.
Secondly, we can let them
through and trap them
once they're inside.
Which do you prefer?
[TRIFE] It's not my style to
spend a long time in battle.
Get rid of them as
quickly as possible.
[KAHYUL] So you want to
go ahead with Plan A?
Stop them from
entering the Gate?
[TRIFE] Correct. It's not going
to be pleasant for them
being wiped out of existence!
[KAHYUL]
Roger.
[ SUURUBILSH CREW A]
The enemy space-time bubbles
are now within range!
In that case,
prepare to fire the mines!
There's a message coming
through from the enemy!
What does it say?
[ SUURUBILSH CREW B]
The enemy wishes to surrender.
Surrender? Are you absolutely
sure that's what it says?
Yes sir, and they're repeating
the message right now.
We couldn't have asked
for a better solution.
This way we don't have to risk
suffering any casualties.
Look, I don't need
you to tell me that!
[TRIFE] What I don't
understand is this:
Why did they try and escape
in the first place if all
they were going to do was
surrender once they got here?
I don't know.
But we've got to deal with
the situation as best we can.
What about trying to
persuade the enemy
to withdraw their
offer of surrender?
[TRIFE] That sounds too
complicated to me.
How about I simply
refuse to accept?
Is that really what
you want to do?
[TRIFE grunts] This is
so frustrating! I can't do that!
I wish I understood what
these guys were up to.
Do you think they honestly
believed they could
escape from us?
Well, they did manage to keep
a few of our frontline forces
busy by making us tail them,
albeit temporarily.
If I were their
supreme commander,
I'd commend them
for their actions.
If they fight, their forces
will be virtually wiped out
and they'll hardly make
a dent in our firepower.
Surrender seems like the
only rational response.
Tell the enemy commander
he'll be pleased to know
he made the right decision.
Of course, sir.
Just say they did succeed
in taking out a few
of our frontline ships.
If their main fleet isn't around
to take advantage of our
weakened position, then what
would be the point?
That's not really the
responsibility of the
enemy ships we're dealing with.
All right.
But if that's true, then what's
the point of us being here?
They're gonna make us look
like a bunch of idiots!
Argh. We've spent all this
time and energy following them
and they don't even
want to fight with us!
You don't have to be
so hard on yourself.
I'm not being hard on myself,
it's the truth!
You know, we were only
following orders.
If you want to blame anyone,
you should blame those back
at Operation
Hunter Headquarters.
They're the ones who made us
come out here on this mission.
I already know that, okay?!
Just for once, I'd appreciate
it if you'd stop telling me
what I already know.
It's very annoying!
[KAHYUL]
I'm sorry.
Tell all squadrons to stop
preparations for battle.
Put all the mines
back into storage
and turn off power
to the laser cannons.
We might as well cancel
the victory celebrations,
while we're at it!
[TRIFE] Step down from battle
stations and get some rest!
I'm going to lie down.
I'll leave all the other
details for you to deal with.
By the way, don't forget
to congratulate
the enemy commander
on his decision.
Yes, Sir. I'll get right on it.
But if you don't mind, I think
it might be a good idea if we
kept the victory
celebrations as planned.
I mean, we did still win,
even though we didn't
actually fight a battle.
Do you mean you'd actually
planned to celebrate in advance?
No, but if your Highness had
wanted to celebrate victory
with a banquet,
we needed to be prepared.
The enemy would not
appreciate your presumption!
In that case what do you want
us to do with everything
we've planned for
the celebration?
[TRIFE]
Well then, prepare the banquet.
But I will not authorize
anything above the bare minimum.
We still have to justify
all our expenses
to the Fleet Accountant,
you know.
But what about if
everybody chips in?
I appreciate the loyalty
and goodwill of our men,
but we don't want
to appear stingy.
Why should they have to
dip into their own pockets
to celebrate a victory
for the Empire?
There's no way I could possibly
allow our men to do that.
[KAHYUL]
Understood.
[NEREIS]
Tenth day of the Month of Keefu.
Operation Hunter is
now in its final stages.
Three weeks ago, the enemy
forces who had tried
to escape through our
weakened front line,
or at least what
was left of them,
were hunted down by Admiral
Trife and the 21st Fleet.
Surrender was their only option.
Of the other enemy fleets
fighting on various fronts,
many soon followed suit.
Those who foolishly tried to
resist didn't live to regret it.
And now we, the Fourth Fleet
of the Imperial Star Forces,
are about to return
to the Star System
where our journey started.
Commander in Chief!
We're going to arrive at the
Vascotton Gate any moment now.
The area appears to be
clear of any enemy ships.
The Vascotton Gate?
So, we've come full circle.
Back to where it all began.
Yes, this was the System
that the Allied forces used
to launch the first
attack on the Empire.
I guess you could say that this
was where the war was born.
In which case,
we've returned to its cradle.
Now... I want you to issue an
order to our front line ships
to fire their reserve mines.
Are you sure that's
going to be necessary?
I mean, the enemy's
nowhere in sight.
A bit of scouting
should be sufficient.
[NEREIS] We can't discount the
possibility that they might have
created an orbital fortress.
[NEFEE]
But, Nereis, don't you remember?
Our reserve mines are virtually
useless on orbital fortresses.
[NEREIS] I just want to
be careful, that's all.
[NEFEE]
Why are you doing this now?
You're usually the last
one to be cautious.
[NEREIS] You've never
been very good at judging
people's character, have you?
[NEFEE] You certainly
can't judge your own.
[NEREIS]
I don't care what you think.
Fire the reserve mines!
[NEFEE] Couldn't you at least
do it on a smaller scale?
[NEREIS]
What's wrong with you?
Why are you being
such a cheapskate?
It's not like we've got to pay
for the mines ourselves!
[NEFEE] It doesn't matter
whose money it is.
I don't like to
see things wasted.
[NEREIS] This Operation's
been a long one.
Why can't we finish it off with
a bang? With a bit of color?
What I'd really love to do is
have all the ships fire their
mines into Plane Space, not just
those in the front line!
[NEFEE] But you won't even
see the explosions in there!
If you want color, why don't
you let off a few fusion bombs
in regular space?
It's also cheaper.
That may well be true.
However...
That's really not
the point here.
I want you to fire the mines.
If you insist. Just remember
I advised you it was
a complete waste
of time and effort...
You see? We're not
getting any response.
[NEREIS]
Reconnaissance squadron!
You may enter the
Vascotton Gate.
Transmission coming through!
No sign of enemy ships
in the Vascotton System!
[NEFEE chuckles]
As far as I remember, I don't
think I actually said we'd find
any enemies in there, did I?
I was simply preparing
for the worst,
taking my responsibility
as commander seriously.
Oh, did you hear
me say anything?
You didn't need to with that
annoyingly smug look of triumph
written all over your face.
Me? Smug? I don't think so.
[ SUKAKAU COMM. CHIEF]
Hold on, the message continues.
It confirms that there's
a large number
of Allied ships in the System!
Allied ships? Where the
hell did they come from?
Isn't it obvious? They must have
come via the Iryuush Kingdom.
Damn it! Why didn't anybody
tell me about this earlier?
If I remember, you were
somewhat obsessed about us
arriving here first.
[NEREIS] Yes, but only
because I wanted the moment
we conquered the Vascotton
System to be the pinnacle,
the climax of the story!
Our efforts have been wasted!
The climax of what story?
The second installment
of my memoirs, of course.
Of course, how silly of me!
How could I possibly not have
realized that that
was what you meant?!
Wandering into the System after
it has already been conquered
by another squadron is hardly
blockbuster material, is it?
This fixation on your memoirs
and your quest for fame
is completely childish!
I'd be so embarrassed
if word got out that the Bebaus
family only finds honor
in being the first
to do something.
I don't want my reputation
tarred with that brush!
[NEREIS]
What's childish about it?
And another thing. If people
start to assume it's a family
tradition to enter into battle
for the sole purpose of making
our memoirs more
dramatically interesting,
then I'm afraid I'll have
to disown the Bebaus name!
It's one thing for the Bebaus
family to have a reputation for
"Spectacular Insanity",
but this isn't spectacular,
it's just insane!
You mean to say you're actually
embarrassed by all this?
That must be a novel
feeling for you!
I would prefer to go
back a few generations
and try to stop the embarrassing
behavior at its source.
But I can't, so I'm
stuck with you.
How wise of you to
realize that, brother.
Enough talk. Now you finally
know what the situation here.
Shouldn't you be giving
us some orders?
Yes, you're right.
All ships! We will now
make a formal entrance
to the Vascotton Gate!
[NEREIS]
Transmit a message to the enemy!
Uh, sorry, I mean to
the Allied flagship.
Roger that.
I wonder who's in
charge of that squadron.
[BOTH gasp]
This is Admiral Abriel,
Commander in Chief
of the Second Fleet, known as
the Light Snow Fleet.
I am Admiral Bebaus,
Commander in Chief
of the Fourth Fleet
of Operation Hunter.
It's truly a great honor
to meet you at last,
your Royal Highness.
However unexpected this
meeting between us is
I assure you the sentiment
is reciprocated.
I would like to ask
a question, sir.
As you've obviously already
gained control of this system,
why didn't you send a patrol
ship into Plane Space
to keep guard? We could
have saved ourselves
a lot of mines if we'd
known you were here.
[NEFEE chuckles] In other words,
firing those mines was really
a waste of time, wasn't it?
We havee only just arrived in
the System ourselves, Admiral.
We were about to send a patrol
ship out into Plane Space
as you suggest, but suddenly
there was this large storm
of mine explosions.
We owe a great debt of
gratitude to the person
who invented the friend or
foe identification system.
Without that, there would have
been no way we could have
escaped serious casualties
from your mines.
By the way, I gather that
my daughter is currently
under your command,
Admiral Bebaus.
Please accept my apologies
for the mine attack.
As for your daughter, well, she
is no longer under my command.
Why? Has she done
something wrong?
[NEREIS]
Not at all.
She's the Territorial Ambassador
for the Lobnas System.
This appears to be of
more interest to her
than active military service
and I think she intends
to continue with it.
That doesn't seem like her.
Are you sure that's right?
Yes. About three weeks ago we
withdrew our military presence
from the area, but then she
requested a leave of absence
with the intention of
heading back there again.
A leave of absence?
Oh, nobody told me.
[NEREIS] We're uploading the
information to your ship now.
Once that has been completed,
you'll be able to find
out all the details.
Thank you, I will. But I think
that's enough about my daughter
for now. I'd be interested to
hear what your next movements
are going to be.
We're awaiting
further orders from
Operation Hunter Headquarters.
I see. Well, until you actually
receive those orders,
I know what you can do.
I suggest your fleet stays and
monitors this System for us.
That will enable our fleet to
head for the Voorash System
without delay.
But sir, wait a moment!
What about the
Territorial Ambassador?
Who's going to supply that?
[DUBUS] I'll leave that
entirely up to you.
With respect, your Highness
gained control of this system
first and therefore it would
make sense for you to provide
the Ambassador from your fleet!
Well, as far as I can see,
I think that you have a number
of suitable candidates, Admiral.
In fact, why don't you take
up the position yourself
while you wait for
your next orders?
I was forced to undertake the
role myself when I was younger,
and I have to admit I found
it exceedingly boring.
I think it might be a
good experience for you
to find out for yourself exactly
how dull a job it can be.
Oh, do you really?
There are some
people who enjoy it.
I wish you all
the best, Admiral!
[NEREIS] But I won't
have anyone to fight.
Oh, you'll have a fierce
opponent waiting for you.
Called boredom. Now if
you'll excuse me...
[NEREIS]
Take care, sir.
[DUBUS] As soon as our fleet
has finished regrouping,
we'll head back through
Keishu Gate 193.
Our next destination will
be the Voorash System.
And after Voorash,
we'll finally be in a position
to recapture the Hyde System.
[DUBUS] And at last I may
be able to repay the debt
I owe to that young man.
[EKURYUA]
I don't like cats. They get old.
They may not look
any different day by day,
but before you know it,
old age creeps up on them
and they don't want to
play with you anymore.
They just want to lay
around sleeping all day.
[EKURYUA]
Yuluvia! Yuluvia!
Then one day,
you discover they've
gone to sleep forever.
[whimpers]
[EKURYUA] We had many
cats at our home,
but he was the only one
who belonged to me.
And he was the one who died.
After that, I swore I'd
never have a cat again.
So, in the end, he didn't
come back to us. did he?
[EKURYUA]
I wonder if he's still alive?
Or if he's gone
to sleep forever.
The Abh grow old in a very
different way from cats.
Our bodies don't look as
though they age at all.
But gradually, we sleep longer
and longer each night.
Until finally we
never wake up again.
[EKURYUA] I've always wondered
how human beings grow old.
Like a cat? Or more like an Abh?
I wanted to ask him about it.
About exactly what it
felt like to grow old.
But how could he possibly
know anything about it?
He's still too young
to give me an answer.
He was the first human I
met who was about my age.
I've always wondered which was
the more peaceful way to go.
Like Yuluvia, my cat,
or like an Abh...
Like my grandfather.
Jinto... are you still alive?
Or have we lost you already?
And if you have gone,
will I feel the same grief I
felt when my grandfather died?
[footsteps]
[JINTO]
I must keep going...
I must... keep going.
I have to survive. I want things
to be like they were before.
When we were children,
able to play.
When you didn't have to bear
the burden of responsibility.
When... I didn't even
really know who I was.
Those were precious times.
I know we can't turn
back the clock,
but you and I, we can be
like that together again.
I can do it.
So... I have to keep going...
As long as I live,
I'll keep going.
Somewhere out there...
You're somewhere out there.
I must keep going...
[JINTO]
I must keep going... Lafiel...
[JINTO] In my sleep, I kept
having these dreams.
I always dreamed I was on the
ground looking up at the stars.
I saw Martine...
I saw Dirkoto... I saw Clasbul.
although some images were
familiar to me from pictures
I'd seen, others were
completely new to me.
And every time I
dreamed this dream,
standing beside me was...