[TREKSES CREW 1]
This is the Star Forces
Transport Ship Trekses.
Leaving port.
[GROUND CONTRO] The route
ahead is free of obstruction.
You are cleared to
prepare for take off.
Thank you. Commence preparations
for take off!
[TREKSES CAPTAIN] This is
a message from the bridge of
the Trekses for all those
of you who are emigrating.
In a moment we will be taking
off and you will experience
approximately twice the
normal level of gravity.
Once we arrive in our satellite
orbit, you will be momentarily
weightless until we can
re-adjust our gravity control.
Please remain calm at all times.
--[gasps]
--[CROWD murmurs]
Heading toward take off area.
[GROUND CONTROL]
Trekses! You have permission
to take off as soon as you
have passed the airship.
[TREKSES CREW 2]
Preparations complete.
Starting the engines!
Twenty seconds until take off.
[TREKSES CREW 2]
Engine output at 75 per cent.
All systems operational.
[TREKSES CREW 1] We are now at
optimum speed for take off.
[TREKSES CREW 3]
Ten seconds to take off.
Eight... Seven... Six... Five...
Four... Three... Two... One...
And take off!
[JINTO] So now we've managed
to move over 15,000 people.
Everything's going
according to plan.
[EKURYUA]
Roger.
[JINTO]
Right, what's next...
[JINTO yelps]
[JINTO]
Ow!
What is it?
I've been attacked!
By a prisoner?
[JINTO]
Everything's fine.
Its weapons are
fairly primitive... Ouch!
Are you okay down there?
[JINTO] This thing's got
thorns all over its body.
Whoa! It just spat at me!
Have I got this right?
It has weapons,
thorns on its body, and spits?
[JINTO]
Oh no! There's more of them!
Ow! Ouch! Get off me!
Is it a rebellion?
[SAMSON laughs]
[SAMSON] It might be more
interesting if it was!
[EKURYUA]
This is Assault Ship Basroil .
We are commencing coupling
with Orbital Station 10885.
The first pressurization
bay is ready to dock.
[LAFIEL] Looks like we're
here for the long haul.
I guess the fact that they've
sent an orbital station
instead of a
human administrator,
means that HQ believes this is
going to be a long-term mission.
[LAFIEL]
Yes, I suppose we're going to
have to be ready for anything.
[SOBAASH] It's been two months
since we arrived in this system.
I'm actually quite glad they've
sent this orbital station.
It helps to break the monotony.
[EKURYUA]
Captain!
Transfer operations from the
Trekses are starting now.
[LAFIEL]
Deploying the transport ships
one after another really
helps speed things along.
You have to admit
that Fleet Command
is handling
this very nicely.
[SOBAASH] Well, yes. But don't
you think it's a bit strange?
What do you mean?
Didn't you notice?
That communication ship we
deployed the other day
hasn't returned and
has yet to report.
So do you think
something unexpected
might have happened
to them on the way?
It's a possibility. I think
we should assume the worst.
[LAFIEL]
Hmm...
[NEFEE]
Taking a quick nap, Nereis?
Actually I wasn't sleeping.
I was just taking time out
to appreciate some art.
You surprise me. That's the sort
of hobby normal people have.
Interesting... I think
I've felt this before.
However, I'm sure I remember
it having some sort of
music as well.
[NEREIS] Can't you just
enjoy art in its pure form?
Music is an unnecessary
addition for area sensor art.
[NEFEE] What a mediocre
opinion coming from you.
It goes against my conscience
to even argue with you.
But I know what I like
and I like composite art.
[NEREIS] Yes, but I believe
that each individual thing
has a beauty of its own
which is lost when it is
combined with other things.
[NEFEE] That's where
I think you're wrong.
The beauty of art is exactly
how the artist chooses
to synthesize all the
various elements.
[NEREIS]
Enough of this.
I'm sure you didn't
come here to ruin
my relaxation with
your opinions about art.
No. We've received a report
I think you should know about.
[NEREIS]
Good news?
[NEFEE] That depends
on how you look at it.
[NEREIS] If I said I
don't want to hear it,
would you be surprised?
[NEFEE]
Of course.
[NERIES]
Huh?
[NEFEE] As long as you let
us handle the situation.
No, wait! You'd better tell me!
It's funny, but I thought
you'd say that.
We've spotted an enemy fleet
passing through Ryureem Gate 13.
There appear to be 40 squadrons.
[NEREIS]
Which way are they heading?
[NEFEE] Towards the Milky
Way Gate, of course.
With the intention of escaping.
[NEREIS]
What?
You mean they aren't planning
to surround and destroy us?
[NEFEE] The enemy commander
obviously has far more
common sense than you.
[NEREIS] What a pity.
Ever since Aptic, I've grown
rather fond of fighting
in defense of the Empire!
Is that why you insisted
on advancing forward
despite all our advice
and pleas to stop?
Our troops aren't
your puppets, Nereis.
Of course, there's no way I
would endanger their lives
without good reason.
So long as our fleet is
keeping the enemy occupied,
the overall losses will
be kept to a minimum.
I was under the impression I'd
already explained that to you.
[NEFEE] You're talking
about overall losses
to Operation Hunter.
But your responsibility
is to the Fourth Fleet.
[NEREIS]
I'm disappointed, Nefee.
Are you saying it's okay as
long as you're not in danger?
[NEFEE] Alright then, if I can't
persuade you to see things from
my point of view,
have you thought about
what the enemy might think?
Actually I have
thought of that.
Even if ultimately
they're not going to win,
if we let them surround
us for a while,
they'll feel like they've
achieved something.
In my memoirs I think I'm going
to write something along
the lines of, "We were
preparing to be annihilated
by a worthy foe."
What do you want
to write that for?
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
I knew that suffering from
a lack of common sense
was one of your many
character flaws,
but I didn't realize
you had no insight.
The reason I want to write that
in my memoir is because--
[NEFEE] Is because you want any
enemy survivors reading your
memoir to be filled with
pride that their battles
were not in vain.
Something along those lines?
So you did understand what
I was saying after all.
I was starting to get
worried about you.
I was vainly hoping you wouldn't
be capable of acting
in such an evil way
Evil? That's a very strong word.
I know deep down you're
concerned about the welfare
of your troops,
in your own way.
That's right. Although I worry
about exactly what you mean by,
"in your own way."
You're actually worried?
It's not like you at all.
But whatever you do, don't think
you have an obligation
to be considerate towards me.
Since when have I
ever made an effort
to be considerate
towards you?
Never. At least not that
I've noticed, anyway.
[NEREIS]
Exactly.
I'll try my best to
carry on just like that.
[NEFEE]
Well that's a relief.
Shouldn't we be deciding what
to should about the enemy?
[NEREIS]
You're right.
I don't want to give them
the impression that I simply
allowed them to get away.
Then again, maybe I
shouldn't write about
this incident at all.
Let's just forget about
these stupid memoirs
for a moment, shall we?
What I was asking was: how shall
we deal with this enemy fleet?
Isn't there anything
left for us to do here?
Something we need
to take care of?
I don't suppose there're
any other squadrons
near the enemy's current route?
[NEFEE] No. Both the supply
ships and the front line ships
are too far away. The enemy is
passing throught the huge gap
between them. But are
you sure you don't want
to go after them?
[NEREIS]
Will you just stop?
I'm sure the General Fleet
will deal with it.
The enemy knows
that their escape
is a last ditch act
of desperation.
If we were to go after them,
it would appear as though
we were bullying the weak.
[NEFEE] They aren't as
weak as you think.
[NEREIS] All the more reason
not to attack, Nefee.
Chasing after them would
be a waste of time.
What's the point in risking
losses to our own side?
Besides, I don't want to give my
readers the impression that
I staged this whole
thing as some sort of
quick fix for the situation.
Can't you be serious about
the situation for a moment?
Now you don't want
us to do anything?
Well, maybe we should let
the command in Dalmav
know about this. And we should
order all those squadrons
behind us to not try
anything stupid.
They should retreat if
looks like the enemy
might launch an attack.
As for us, we'll keep
pushing forward.
Especially now we know there
aren't any enemy forces
ahead of us.
Besides the other fleets
will find out about
the enemy's movements soon
and the competition
will get even tougher.
Wait. What are you saying?
You want us to be the
first ones to arrive?
[NEREIS]
It would be a great honor.
You see, Nefee?
I have the honor of the Fourth
Fleet at heart after all.
[KUFADIS] Looking at all the
information we have gathered,
it appears the enemy forces have
slipped through the front line
at the Milky Way Gate
and are now advancing towards
the center of the system.
[KUFADIS] They are periodically
stealing fuel from the civilian
anti-matter factories
in the area,
which is delaying
their progress.
But even taking
that into account,
they still aren't
traveling very fast.
Their escape is probably being
hindered by the slow moving
supply squadrons
accompanying them.
In the end it all--
Now let me guess.
The enemy fleet would like to be
reunited with its main fleet?
It is the most likely strategy.
[SPOOR] Is that so? There was
little old me thinking
they wanted to
abandon their fleet.
What would they do once
they'd abandoned it?
[SPOOR] They could go
down to the ground world
and do whatever they
liked down there.
Unlike us, they don't have
any particular reason
to carry on being in space.
In this case it looks
like they do.
[KUFADIS] They also have a need
to protect their interests.
And will instinctively
fight to the end
to achieve that goal.
Surely every soldier
thinks like that.
Of course, there are
always exceptions.
Have we finished everything
here that we need to do?
[KUFADIS] According to the
orders that we were given,
our job is to continue observing
what's left of the enemy forces.
In addition to that, we are
to continue patrolling
the front lines and report back.
Okay, I know, I know.
But there's nothing
really for us do!
The war in Operation Hunter
is effectively over.
[KUFADIS]
You could well be right.
We may not have much of the
enemy left to deal with now,
but until we are able to conquer
all of the territories within
the sphere of Operation Hunter;
until we are able to reclaim all
the planets conquered by the
enemy four years ago;
the war will still be going on.
[KUFADIS] I thought she had set
her heart on fighting a battle
no matter what the circumstance,
but maybe she'll just stay
safely behind the
scenes this time.
You suddenly look
very happy, Chief.
[KUFADIS]
Huh? Oh no!
It's just the mission
seems to have settled down.
I'm glad it makes you so happy.
For me it's just more
boredom as usual.
Nothing to do but sit and wait.
[YAWNS]
[SPOOR] I suppose we should
prioritize observing
the remnants of the enemy
fleet as they escape.
When are you going to supply
the operation plans?
Would you be willing to
give authorization for us
to start moving in the same
direction as the enemy fleet?
[SPOOR]
Of course, Chief of Staff.
Then we'll leave in
the next six hours.
[SPOOR] But make sure that we,
here on the flagship,
are accompanied by as
many ships as possible.
[KUFADIS] So she is planning to
enter into battle after all.
Did you hear me?
[KUFADIS]
Uh! Yes Ma'am!
[TRIFE]
Why exactly did the Fourth Fleet
let the enemy slip
past them like that?
[KAHYUL] I expect they simply
didn't respond quickly enough.
[TRIFE]
Really? If that's the case,
then there's nothing we
can do about it now.
Hm. But they didn't even
try to go after them.
They made no effort whatsoever.
I don't understand. What was
Admiral Bebaus thinking?!
If they'd gone after them,
they'd have suffered heavy
losses and gained very little.
I expect they realized this
and I believe they
made a sensible choice.
It may have been sensible,
but I don't agree it
was the right choice.
If they had annihilated the
remainder of the enemy fleet,
Operation Hunter would
have been complete.
We could still do it...
But I only have 43
squadrons at my command.
It's possible that the main
fleet of the Triple Alliance
could synchronize its forces
to attempt some sort of
pincer movement against the
enemy ships that are remaining.
But if we simply station a large
detachment on the front line,
then that will give a signal
to the enemy's command
that some of their fleet is
trying to escape from us.
[TRIFE] I see. I do understand
what you're saying.
It makes sense.
But I'm still not satisfied.
[KAHYUL]
The enemy has 40 squadrons.
That's too many for us to say
that we would have a sure
advantage if we attacked.
But they likely have a large
number of supply ships
within those 40 squadrons.
The chances are good
that their actual firepower
is a lot less than ours.
I agree but we don't
know for sure.
It's pure conjecture
and we shouldn't make
any assumptions now.
[KAHYUL] Very well.
In that case we need to wait
for a reconnaissance
report from Admiral Spoor.
[TRIFE] It's possible we may
not get the information in time
before we have to fight. We have
no idea what may happen.
[KAHYUL] Discovering the
strength of the enemy forces
is a top priority for the
reconnaissance missions.
There's no way they'd allow
us to enter into battle
without the appropriate
intelligence information.
We can't rely too
heavily on that.
There's a long tradition between
the commanders in the Star
Forces of being uncooperative
toward each other.
[KAHYUL]
Come on.
Calling it a tradition
is going a bit too far.
Damn it! What do I care
if the enemy's command
finds out that there
are survivors?
All I'm interested in is getting
enough of our forces together
to annihilate what's left
of them! It's that simple!
If only I had double the
strength right now...
I see...
And what exactly do
you mean by that?
Just that I think
I'm beginning to see
what you meant
about the tradition
of being uncooperative
with each other.
That's all I meant.
Nothing more, nothing less.
That's good. I'm so
pleased you understand.
Yes, it's all becoming
crystal clear to me now.
I'm relieved to hear it.
We should plan our strategy
on the assumption that
the entire enemy fleet is
made up of elite forces.
We therefore need to
think carefully before
attacking them head on.
I hope you don't mind me asking,
but are you feeling well?
Yes, I've never felt better.
What's the point
of your question?
You have to admit it's
rather unusual for
your Excellency to
be so cautious.
What else do you suggest I
do? Attack our allies
so I can commandeer
the use of their ships?!
I would strongly
advise you against
taking that course of action.
I wouldn't want to put myself
in the unfortunate position
of having to charge my
senior officer with treason.
Maybe you should simply wait
and let someone else charge me.
Save yourself the trouble.
[KAHYUL]
What for?
[TRIFE]
Hmph.
Never mind. We'll stick with
a mobile defense pattern
and each time we inflict
damage on the enemy ships,
we'll retreat again.
I want you to plan our
strategy with that in mind.
Yes sir, right away.
[JINTO] You want us to
suspend the emigration?
[LAFIEL] Yes, the communication
ship from the Fourth Fleet
has arrived.
We've been ordered to evacuate
the area temporarily.
[JINTO] I know that if the
enemy is in the vicinity,
we should do everything we can
to avoid any risk of attack.
[JINTO sighs] But it's going to
be hard to convince all these
people of that...
The plan is for us to withdraw
from the area on the 17th
standard day and then to
return again on the 60th day.
Tell the people that we intend
to continue with the emigration
process as soon as we return.
Well, okay.
I'll try to do my best.
This is irresponsible!
You come here saying
you'll help us
and then leave us at
a moment's notice!
It's unacceptable!
Absolutely! You've gone
and ruined my chances
of getting off this planet!
No... you see--
[MEIDEEN] What you don't realize
is that most of the staff's
families have already
been shipped
to your prisoner of war camps.
If we suspend the
emigration now,
the staff may never see
their wives, husbands,
or their children again!
I know that the Abh don't hold
families in high regard,
but for us it's different!
For some of our people, being
separated from their family
is a fate worse than death!
This is only temporary.
We'll be back as soon as we can!
[MEIDEEN]
How do we know we can trust you?
The only information we
get on what's happening
in space is from you.
It's possible that you're
keeping something from us.
You say it's only temporary,
but maybe you're never
going to return!
Which would leave the planet
open for the United Mankind
to come back and take
control once more.
If that happens, the staff and
their families will be living
under the control
of different nations
who are at war with each other!
Can't you understand
what that means?
[JINTO]
Huh?
Actually... I do understand.
Given the current circumstances,
I believe the best course of
action would be if we were
the ones who took priority
in the emigration.
Because once the United
Mankind comes back
and takes control,
it's almost guaranteed
we'll be treated just
like criminals again.
Treated like criminals?
What arrogance!
You are criminals!
You have been proven guilty
beyond any reasonable doubt!
You're prisoners!
[JINTO]
Ahem.
[MEIDEEN]
Whatever happens,
we have no power to
stop you leaving.
But we ask that you finish
the emigration before you do.
Before you evacuate,
we want you to ensure
that we are all moved
off this planet.
Please don't forget
to take us as well.
I understand your concerns.
We'll do our best.
[MEIDEEN]
Do your best?! Is that all?!
[JINTO]
That's all.
Until we know what's happening
with the transport ship,
we can't tell if we will be
able to move all the people
who wish to emigrate before
the deadline for evacuation.
[MEIDEEN] I insist that you
help us emigrate before then!
[JINTO] I find it hard to
understand what you,
as the Territorial
Representative,
are so worried about.
I know that some of your staff
have already been moved off
the planet, but you allowed all
their families and the less
important staff to
leave first, right?
As far as I can see, you still
have all the people and supplies
you need to run the island
efficiently for at least
another two months.
[MEIDEEN] But we have no
guarantee that it will only
be two months
before you return!
Shall I tell you what the
Administrative Director
is afraid of? What's really
behind all this?
What? What is it?
[MEIDEEN] Why don't you
save your breath?!
I intend to nominate
you as the next
Territorial Representative.
Think about the honor
of this planet!
[SHANGAL]
The honor of this planet?!
That's about right.
What would the Territorial
Deputy Ambassador give me
in return for my information?
Well, it's not something I think
I want to concern myself with.
That's a shame.
Now what's all this about being
Territorial Representative,
Mr. Director? I thought you
didn't like the title?
I don't mind you taking my title
of Territorial Representative
because then you won't
sully the good name
of the office of the
Administrative Director.
And it won't be
for long, anyway.
So you do believe
we'll be coming back.
[MEIDEEN]
That's not the point.
If the Abh don't return,
then we'll be under the control
of the United Mankind
and the title of
Territorial Representative
will become redundant.
If that happens I may not
see my family again...
I see. Try to believe
we'll do our best.
That's all I can promise
for the time being.
Well, I don't suppose
we have much choice.
After all, you're in charge.
[JINTO]
I guess he's right...
[LAFIEL] Three more days
until we evacuate.
[JINTO] In the end, things
didn't go according to plan.
[JINTO]
This is beautiful.
I wish she could be
here to see this view.
[LAFIEL]
It's been a long time...
...since we actually saw
each other in person.
--[beeping]
--[JINTO] Huh?
[MEIDEEN] Is that His
Excellency the Count?
Yes.
[MEIDEEN]
It's a rebellion!
We need your
assistance immediately!
[JINTO]
Hm? Yes. I'm on my way.
This is how it should be.
[shouting, grunting]
We're under attack!
We need help!
So you thought you were
gonna leave without us?!
Your leaving women
behind for us!
[PRISON GUARDS yell]
[PRISONERS yell]
Take that, suckers!
[SAMSON]
Come on everybody!
I thought I told you guys this
was not a recreational trip!
Oh Line Wing Aviator...
I can't drink anymore.
[SAMSON] Of all the times to
get drunk, they choose now!
[grunts]
The Eastern Detention
Sector has launched an attack
against the Central
Detention Sector.
Huh? What happened to
all the armed guards?
What do you think?
They're fighting back!
But if that's the case,
then we havent got
anything to worry about.
Their weapons must
have been home made.
They can't be as powerful as
regular weapons, can they?
[MEIDEEN] They have
regular weapons as well!
But how did that happen?
Well, we have a traitor
in our midst.
Someone among the staff
who wanted to stay behind.
Administrative Director,
do you mean to say
that the leader is...
You're right. I don't
need to tell you.
It's him.
[ANGUS chuckles]
[SHANGAL]
Huh?
[MEIDEEN] I just don't
understand the logic that these
prisoners are using
in this situation!
[SHANGAL] Don't treat me like
I'm one of Angus's men.
--[JINTO] Uh...
--[SHANGAL] Huh?
If there's anything
we can do to help you
resolve this situation,
we're ready to help.
[JINTO] I thought I
learned my lesson in Aptic
that being a hero
wasn't really my style.
[TOMASOF] So now the
second wall is being attacked
from two sides: the Eastern
and the Central Sectors!
I think this is becoming
too interesting...