[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
Captain! An electromagnetic wave
is heading directly for us
from the planet below!
Hostile attack?
[EKURYUA]
It's coming straight at us!
Now there's another one!
This one's from one of
the planet's satellites!
[gasps] Another!
The magnetic shield hasn't
reached its full power yet.
[EKURYUA]
And now another!
Hold on a minute...
Their power output is too
weak for it to be an attack.
What is it? A transmission?
[EKURYUA]
Could be.
I've just identified
the conversion format,
so we can find out.
[BOTH sigh]
You shouldn't scare
me like that.
We now have four
different requests
for communication coming in.
Our priority is the
territorial government.
This is odd. All the
transmissions are saying
they're representatives of
the territorial government.
[JINTO, LAFIEL]
Huh?
Why not open all of them?
We can't listen to four
people at the same time!
If you'll let me, I don't
mind givin' it a try.
Okay, then.
Second Aviator!
Open up all four of the
transmission circuits.
Stop being... so bossy.
No, I'm not really...
I'm just wearing my Territorial
Deputy Ambassador hat.
[EKURYUA]
It's on.
[JINTO]
Huh?
[ALL chattering]
[EKURYUA]
This is the bridge.
Preparations to launch
the Calike are complete.
Roger. This is the Calike.
All systems okay to go.
Start propulsion.
Engines activated.
You are cleared for departure.
Departing.
Jinto...
[PEOPLE chattering]
[JINTO]
Excuse me, please!
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the Territorial
Deputy Ambassador, Count Hyde.
By my side is the
Territorial Ambassador,
her Highness the
Viscountess Paryunu.
I have to admit that we
find this a little confusing
and I hope you understand why.
We didn't expect
a single territory
to have four different
governments.
So therefore...
[ALL chattering]
Will you all please
be quiet for a second!
As you may have already
gathered, we have all four
of your transmission circuits
open at the same time.
[MEIDEEN] What made
you do such a thing?
[JINTO] We assumed it would
be the simplest way for us
to get an accurate
overview of the situation.
I hope it was the
right decision.
[JINTO growls]
[JINTO] Now, we'd like
each of you to take turns
explaining to us
why you're here.
My name is Geol Meideen.
I am the Administrative
Director of Lobnas II.
Now that our planetary system
has regrettably been brought
under the control of
the Empire, I believe
that my job requires me to
represent the interests of
our inhabitants in their
dealings with you.
[JINTO] What happened
to the Prime Minister?
[MEIDEEN]
Lobnas II has no Prime Minister.
Its constitution is unique in
that the Administrative Director
may act as the
Executive Officer,
when appointed directly by
the Central Government.
This position is
currently held by me.
Oh, I see.
My name is Yuuri Dokufu
and I hold a rightful claim
to the position of Prime
Minister of the Lobnas System.
Huh? But that appears to
contradict what Mr. Meideen
has just told me...
[DOKUFU] It's merely a
difference of interpretation.
I was elected as the
result of an impartial,
free and fair election.
As opposed to some "official"
who was assigned here
by the Central Government
only a year ago.
How can you say that?!
You only started claiming
to be Prime Minister
about three hours ago!
And another thing!
It was hardly a "free
and fair" election!
The only people who were able
to vote were your cronies!
[DOKUFU]
Anyone on the electoral register
was able to cast their vote.
[MEIDEEN]
Exactly! Only your cronies
qualified to get
on the register!
Uh, maybe... we should move
on to the next person?
[SHANGAL] I, too, am Prime
Minister of the Lobnas System
elected in an
impartial election.
My name is Lala Shangal.
But I would prefer it if you
called me Madam Prime Minister.
I see. Thank you. Hm...
And I suppose you're the
Prime Minister, as well?
[ANGUS] I don't hold
any great store by titles.
I don't need an election.
In any case, it's the
will of God that we
should be in charge of
this planetary system.
After all, we are the
strongest around here.
[JINTO] And, uh, what's
your name, please?
Mikay Angus.
If you didn't win an election,
how can you claim
to be in charge?
By strength, by popularity,
and by the true will of God.
Oh, I see...
Well, I can see you all have
a very complex situation
to deal with here.
I think we'd prefer to wait
until you've sorted everything
out between yourselves.
We haven't got
any time for that!
[JINTO]
Why not?
[MEIDEEN]
Isn't it obvious?
I want you to declare me as
the official representative
so that we can start
receiving support right away!
[JINTO]
What do you mean, support?
[MEIDEEN] Are you saying
it's not possible?
[JINTO] Not necessarily,
but we need to know
what kind of
support you require.
At the very least, we could
offer the basic things
your people need for survival.
[MEIDEEN] In that case,
it would be best if they were
distributed under
the supervision
of the Administrative Agency.
If we need to go through the
official process of surrender
for that to happen,
then let's get on with it.
Our people need food
and they need it quickly.
The only way it's going to be
distributed fairly
is through us.
If you hand the food
over to the others,
it'll just end up in the
mouths of their own people!
That's simply not true!
Everyone on this
planet is our friend.
All supplies will be
distributed equally.
Thereby using the
opportunity to extend
your base of power!
You can't trust men
to do anything!
My duty is to protect all the
women who live on this planet.
A bureaucrat, a man with
no balls, and a woman!
You should choose us.
We're the only ones who
can protect the food
and get it where it's needed!
[MEIDEEN] Listen to them.
You can guess what'll happen
if you hand anything
over to them...
Are you in the middle
of a civil war?
[MEIDEEN] You could say
we're on the verge of it...
Maybe you could explain
what's going on?
[MEIDEEN]
You mean you don't know?!
Well, the majority
of the inhabitants
are actually here as prisoners.
[gasps]
[CREW 15A] Entering the
atmosphere in 30 seconds.
Everyone! Prepare for impact!
[CREW 15B]
Putting the anti-matter
fuel cell into stable mode.
[CREW 15A] All crew are
now prepared for impact.
Gravity control device
is being shut down.
[CREW 15B] We have confirmation
of our descent route.
[CREW 15A] We'll be entering
the atmosphere in 10 seconds.
8...7...6...
...5...
...4...
...3...
...2...
...1...
Entering now!
[JINTO]
So, what you're saying
is that Lobnas II is nothing
more than a huge prison?
We prefer to use the term
"correctional institution."
Well, in that case,
the other three...
Uh, does that mean
they're prisoners?
[DOKUFU] I refuse to accept
such a description!
What is true is that as a result
of the law of the United Mankind
we were forcibly
immigrated to this planet.
But as time goes on,
Lobnas is drifting away
from the authority of
the United Mankind.
[LAFIEL]
Did he not know about this?
Or did he assign me to
this system on purpose?
[ANGUS]
That's right.
It doesn't matter
if we're designated
as prisoners and them
as prison guards!
[LAFIEL]
It must have slipped his mind.
I suggest we hold a
democratic general election,
thereby choosing the proper
representative of the people.
How will you organize
the electoral commission?
What exactly is an
electoral commission?
I can try and explain it to you,
but I don't think it's a job
you'd really want to do.
Are you making fun of me?
Holding an election is
absolutely out of the question!
It's a certainty that a prisoner
would end up being elected!
Because there are far more
prisoners than guards!
But you won't know that
for sure unless you try.
Those of us who
used to be prisoners
are divided in our opinions.
And some of the ex-prison guards
may have different
opinions, too.
They may not want to
vote for Meideen.
[MEIDEEN]
You are still prisoners!
And my men are still on
active duty as prison guards
and don't you forget it!
I think maybe we should
shut down the transmission
for a minute. What do you say?
'Kay.
Cut them off?
I think so.
All right everyone, we need
to discuss this matter.
We will suspend transmission
but please wait for us
to contact you again.
Looks like this is going
to be a tougher assignment
than expected!
Got any ideas?
What do you think we should do?
Well, the most basic
rule in business
is to make sure you're dealing
with the right person.
It doesn't matter who
you arrange a deal with,
however big or small,
if that person is unable
to deliver the goods.
[LAFIEL] So who do you think
can deliver the goods here?
[SOBAASH] If anyone's got
the right credentials,
it would be Meideen.
As Administrative Director,
he has access
to information and analysis
about the local population,
as well as having
an administrative
structure in place.
So you mean
we gotta deal with the
guy who's favorite to win?
How boring!
Yeah. I'm with you.
I don't believe this!
I'm not going to make some crazy
decision simply to make life
more exciting for you!
Let's get the Administrative
Director back up on the screen.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure!
That didn't take long.
[LAFIEL]
I've decided to accept you
as the territorial
representative.
You'll see that you have
made the correct decision.
[LAFIEL] If you in turn accept
me as your ambassador,
then we will have completed
all the necessary procedures.
[MEIDEEN]
I accept.
And I request supplies
and aid immediately.
[LAFIEL]
Understood.
Specify a delivery
location for the supplies.
[MEIDEEN] Your assistance
is greatly appreciated.
However, there is something else
I would like to mention...
Go ahead.
Until recently, we have relied
on the armed forces
of the Central Government to
help control the prisoners.
However, your arrival has
meant those forces
have been driven
out of the area.
I have to be honest with you
and say that I'm not confident
we can restrain the
prisoners using
only the police force down
here on the planet.
It's possible we might
be able to provide
some sort of military
assistance.
[MEIDEEN] I don't mean to
question your abilities, but
do you have enough resources
to fight a ground battle?
[JINTO]
A ground battle?
Surely the prisoners
aren't armed?
[MEIDEEN]
Of course, strictly speaking,
the prisoners aren't
allowed to own weapons.
[gunshot]
[MEIDEEN]
However, it appears the rules
haven't always been
enforced with the attention
to detail that they
should have been.
To put it more bluntly, we know
that some of the
prisoners have weapons.
As far as we can tell,
they are fairly primitive,
probably using some sort
of homemade gunpowder.
But they can still be a threat
if used in the right way.
[LAFIEL]
But if there's an uprising,
then we can simply
halt the supply of food.
And if you want, we
could also blow away
a bit of the planet's
atmosphere.
Wouldn't that be enough
to stop the rebellion?
Huh?!
[JINTO clears throat]
When the Abh-- I mean
when we have to take
emergency measures
on a ground world,
there's often a tendency
to be quite excessive
in the use of force.
Please be assured
we bear no ill will
against you, and that,
personally, I think it's wrong
for us to impose such
drastic measures
from space on such delicate
ground worlds as yours.
Really, there's nothing
to be worried about!
But how could a planet
possible recover
from losing its atmosphere?
No matter how justified
the motives are?
[JINTO]
You're right of course.
The only action we'll take
will be to stop food supplies.
We won't launch an attack
on the planet from space
unless specifically
requested by you.
[MEIDEEN]
Why would I do that?!
It would be like
requesting mass suicide!
[JINTO]
But if you let people know
that such action is an option,
won't it help to act
as a deterrent
against rebellion?
[MEIDEEN] I don't suppose
I have much choice.
I will say this to you.
While I appreciate
and am grateful for
the Territorial Ambassador's
efforts to assist,
I have now realized that
the problems of this planet
are of no concern to
the Empire whatsoever.
Thank you.
[CREW 15A] We've just passed
through the ionosphere.
Air stabilization
device activating now!
Landing signals being received
from the Territorial Government.
Territorial Deputy Ambassador?
We'll be landing in
approximately 12 minutes.
Thanks for the information.
Hey! Haven't we arrived yet?
No, but it won't be
too much longer.
Are you sure it's okay
for you to come with me?
Course it is.
These young guys
can handle anything.
With them in charge, the
ship'll be in safe hands.
It's you we've got
to worry about,
and that's why I'm comin'
to look after you.
The planet's one big hive
of vicious criminals, right?
Besides, it's been a while
since I've set foot on land.
Can't let an opportunity
like this slip away!
[JINTO] But there's probably
nothing down there.
There'll be lots of fresh air!
[CREW 15A] Passing through
the stratosphere.
Outside temperature
is decreasing.
[CREW 15C] Our destination has
been confirmed as Lajay Island.
Altitude: two million
daj and falling.
Prepare for splashdown.
[CREW 15B] Float numbers one,
two, and three deployed!
[CREW 15C]
Wind force 0.54.
Our instruments indicate no
need for inertia control.
Speed difference at
ground level: 0.02.
Altitude 5,000 daj.
4,500...
4,000...
3,500...
3,000...
2,500...
2,000...
1,500...
1,000...
500...
[CREW 15C]
Splash down.
[sighs]
[CREW laughing]
[SAMSON]
Ah, yes, this is the life!
Blue skies... blue seas...
Everything you could wish for!
This is great! The smell
of salt in the air!
The smell of salt?
Yup, this is the smell
of the seaside!
Every ocean is
made up of salt water.
Didn't you know that, my boy?
This is the first time
I've ever been to an ocean.
[SAMSON] Really? Well,
this wonderful smell
is proof that this
is the real thing!
Even though
the rest of the planet
is a gloomy prison.
[MEIDEEN]
Welcome to Lobnas II.
[JINTO] It's nice to meet you,
Administrative Director.
If I may, I would like
to say what an honor it is
to meet you face to face,
your Excellency Count Hyde.
And now let me update you
on the current situation.
The only inhabited area on the
planet is here on Lajay Island.
The red area shows you
the detention sector
and the white one the
administrative sector.
Located within the
administrative sector
are various facilities,
accommodations for the prison
guards and their families,
local markets and so on.
Obviously, the detention sector
is where the prisoners
are housed.
And what are these lines here?
[MEIDEEN]
They're actually walls.
On the east side is
the men's sector,
on the west, the women's.
The center sector is mixed.
We call them respectively
the Eastern, the Western,
and the Central
detention sectors.
It's fairly straightforward.
Surely everyone
would want to live
in the Central detention sector?
They first have to fulfill
a certain requirement.
What? Good behavior?
No, not that. They must
undergo sterilization.
Sterilization?!
A bureaucrat, a man
with no balls, and a woman!
You should choose us.
The three who claim
to be Prime Minister--
do they represent each of
the three detention sectors?
That's right.
[JINTO]
So the Western sector must be
represented by Lala Shangal,
the Center by Dokufu,
and the East by Angus?
[MEIDEEN]
Very impressive, Ambassador.
Absolutely correct.
I was just guessing.
Why don't you just sterilize all
of the prisoners on the island?
Force them to be sterilized?
I couldn't possibly do
anything so inhumane!
But if the Empire thinks
that is the best way forward,
who am I to disagree?
We wouldn't do
something like that!
The Empire doesn't like to get
involved in the internal affairs
of the ground worlds.
[MEIDEEN] That's all very well,
but given our situation
we wish you would get involved.
[JINTO]
What do you mean?
[MEIDEEN] I tried the
warning you suggested,
but it didn't seem
to have had any effect.
The prisoners in the Eastern
sector are gathering together
and they are believed
to be armed.
Are you suggesting
that they're planning
some sort of attack on you here?
[MEIDEEN]
It seems increasingly likely.
It is possible that the
men are trying to invade
the Central sector, but
only as a means to an end.
It's becoming apparent that
their final objective is to get
to the women in the
Western detention sector.
[JINTO]
Well, that sounds terrible.
[MEIDEEN] You don't realize the
seriousness of the situation!
Please forgive me,
your Excellency.
[JINTO]
That's okay...
Obviously the women are here
because they are criminals.
However, many of those women
were victims of crime before
they turned to crime themselves.
Being a victim
was often a trigger
that caused them
to change sides.
And for most of them, the
crimes that were committed
against them
were related to sex.
They are here because
they have chosen
to live in a world without men.
You can't trust
men to do anything!
My duty is to protect all the
women who live on this planet!
[JINTO]
I see...
[MEIDEEN]
I want you to protect them.
But... you make it
sound as though
you're intending to relinquish
all responsibility
for what happens
in this situation!
Yes, that's right.
Perhaps I should've been
clearer from the beginning.
All of us here,
the administrative staff,
the guards, their families,
the people who
run the markets.
We intend to seek refuge.
[JINTO]
But, why?!
[MEIDEEN]
I'm sure you can figure it out.
[JINTO] You think the prisoners
may be dangerous enough
to start an uprising?
[MEIDEEN]
Exactly.
[JINTO]
I acknowledge your request.
I'll have to discuss
the issue with
Her Royal Highness the
Territorial Ambassador,
and then come back
to you with a decision.
[MEIDEEN] How can you be
so relaxed about it?
The rebellion could
start at any moment!
Is that what the Empire
wants to happen here?
[JINTO]
I could be wrong,
but an uprising
could still take place
even if you'd
all left the island.
[SAMSON] In fact, if all
the guards have left,
it would mean the probability of
rebellion would likely increase.
[MEIDEEN] I suppose you could
look at it that way.
[JINTO] I don't think you'll
have to wait too long.
We just need to get more of an
understanding of the situation
before we can make
any final decisions.
We'll help you
in any way we can.
[JINTO] What? I thought we
were the ones helping them!
You didn't mention this before,
but do you have any idea
roughly how many people
would be seeking refuge
from the situation?
We can get a detailed
list to you later,
but as far as I remember
it was about 20,000.
20,000...?!
[SOBAASH]
He'll be all right.
Who will be?
Well, it's probably
nothing, but...
This was the time that Supply
Officer Lin was meant
to have started
the conference call.
The Line Wing Aviator's with
him, so we don't need to worry.
[SOBAASH]
Very well...
[LAFIEL]
Isn't it...
Isn't it time for you to go
down to the ground world now?
[JINTO]
What? Already?
I'll be there in a minute.
Do you want me to bring
you back a souvenir?
Idiot.
[JINTO]
I'm sorry, Lafiel...
[SOBAASH]
He will be okay.
Yes.
[JINTO]
Isn't it strange?
That that was our
last conversation.
Our very last...
When what I really
wanted to say was...
But I couldn't find the words.
I'm sorry, Lafiel...
Goodbye, Lafiel...
I wanted to say it,
but I couldn't.
Would you please
stop doing that!
I hope you're not treating
me like a little kid.
What was that you just said?
We're not the prisoners here!
That was slanderous!
This is quite unforgivable.
You say you want
to get out of here,
but at the same time you're
busy making plans to stay.
Not to mention our new society.
--What?!
--[SHANGAL] With Angus?!
Miss Fazun!
We're coming under attack!
This place will soon
be worse than hell.