[JINTO grunts]
[JINTO coughs]
[JINTO] I've lost track of how
many days I've been down here...
I don't know how much longer
I can remain in hiding
from the prisoners. Or even how
much longer I can stay alive.
I ran out of things
to eat some time ago.
I think the last time I
ate I had some Alileem.
But it was so long ago,
I can't be sure.
So I decided I had to
conserve my strength.
I had to make sure I gave
my body complete rest.
Although, to be honest,
I didn't really have
anything else to do.
Unless I could gather enough
strength to steal something
from one of the prisoners.
This is fun! I never realized
robbery could be so exciting!
Neither did I!
Listen up you guys!
We need you to give us all of
your money, or else I'll shoot!
You little punk!
That was fun! I guess you've
actually got to steal
something to be a
successful robber.
Who'd have thought I'd be
doing something like this?
Have you ever stolen anything
from anyone before?!
Oh, you've got to be kidding...
I'm a complete amateur.
[JINTO] When I wasn't sleeping,
I tried to write poetry.
I wanted to leave behind some
evidence of my existence.
[JINTO] Born in darkness,
Died in darkness.
What a cliché!
Not very good, I know.
I don't think I'm ever
going to be remembered
for my literary prowess.
[JINTO gasps]
Wait a second.
Why am I writing in
the Abh language?
Maybe if I wrote my
poetry in Martinese,
it would sound
reasonably good.
Hold on. There's only really one
person I'm writing this for.
And she's not from Martine.
What would she'd say
if my last words were
written in a language
she couldn't understand?
Would she ever know my
true feelings for her?
What if I write some poetry in
Martinese and then translate
it into the Abh language?
No, that wouldn't work.
Besides, the only Martine
poetry I remember is a lullaby.
A lullaby... Maybe that
isn't such a stupid idea.
[JINTO hums]
[JINTO] I'm sorry, Lafiel.
Goodbye, Lafiel...
Captain, are you all right?
[LAFIEL] To be perfectly honest,
not really.
Is this what your world
is like all the time?
I know Lobnas doesn't have a lot
going for it, but I've always
thought the ocean was one of
the best features on Lobnas.
Yes, the sea air is
very refreshing.
Nice weather too!
Unfortunately the Abh are more
used to traveling in space,
than on water.
[TOMASOF chuckles]
[SAMSON]
It's worse than I expected.
We've only been gone three
weeks and there's nothing left.
[TOMASOF] Yes. I expect
the rival factions of
Dokufu and Angus are
still fighting each other.
[SAMSON]
Pretty chaotic, huh?
[TOMASOF]
That's a good word to use.
[TOMASOF] I wonder what's
going to happen to Lobnas II
when all this is over?
[CREW A] 1st squad!
Commence the operation!
[LAFIEL grunts]
[SAMSON]
Where are you going?!
I advise you to stay here,
Captain. It's too dangerous.
I'm here on a personal matter,
which has nothing to do
with you, so let me go!
[SAMSON] Actually it has a lot
to do with me since I took
a leave of absence to
come back here with you.
However, if you do go,
you can't go dressed like that.
You'll stand out too much.
[TOMASOF] I agree.
You'll be to easy a target.
Besides, you helped us
get back on our feet.
And quite frankly,
we can't run the risk of your
Highness getting hurt out there.
If word gets out that we
allowed you to head off
without any protection,
then we'll lose any
credibility we've gained!
Don't worry about me.
I can look after myself.
Your job isn't to protect me.
But even so,
your Highness...
[SAMSON] Captain. If you think
that putting yourself in danger
like this is going to make up
for the decision you made,
you're wrong.
What do you mean by that?
I made the right decision.
I don't have to make
up for anything.
Then there's no reason for you
to risk your life unnecessarily,
is there?
[LAFIEL sighs]
Very well...
[TOMASOF sighs]
In that case,
we would like to continue with
the operation, your Highness.
Yes, go ahead.
It can't be easy
for them, either.
What can't be?
For one thing, the fact that
this used to be their home.
All of those precious
memories destroyed.
I know they chose to evacuate,
but it's still probably a shock
to see devastation
on this scale.
I guess so.
[SAMSON]
Well, time for me to head out.
Where are you going?
I hope you didn't stop me from
looking for him simply so
that you could give yourself
the opportunity to be forgiven.
No, we believe there
are many different ways
for you to repent of your sins.
[LAFIEL]
What do you mean 'we'?
[SAMSON] Well, our traditions
back at home, of course!
[LAFIEL]
What are you going to do?
[SAMSON] Cook! When a friend
returns after being away
for a long time, it's customary
for us to welcome them home
with a delicious meal.
And we go all out to
make it a real feast!
[LAFIEL] You actually brought
your cooking stuff with you?!
[SAMSON] Of course! Why do you
think I wanted to come here
with you in the first place?
After what he's been through,
he deserves a meal equivalent
to someone being
away for ten years!
I just hope we find him
before it all goes cold.
I'd hate to see it go to waste.
Do you know what is one
of the worst faux pas
that you could ever make
on Midgrat? Have a guess!
Uh... Letting food
go to waste?
Close.
Actually, it's to let someone
prepare a meal in your honor
and then forget to go.
Heh. I don't think the
boy would do that to me!
Do you want me to help you?
With cooking the meal, I mean.
You, Captain?!
I... Thanks for the offer,
but Midgrat's style of cooking
is quite unique and requires
knowledge of
traditional methods.
Anyway, I only brought
enough stuff for me to use.
I'll be fine by myself.
I wasn't forcing you.
[SAMSON] I suggest you
leave everything to me.
Besides, if I recall correctly,
you've never cooked before,
have you?
Well no, I haven't
ever cooked before!
But I thought there
might've been something
simple I could do to
help you. Never mind.
I'd better get going.
--[LAFIEL] Wait a minute!
--Huh?
What is it?
Well... I was wondering if you
could tell me what sort of
reaction I should have
when I see him again?
[SAMSON]
Hm?
Of course, that all depends on
exactly who the Captain is going
to be seeing again.
What do you mean?!
I think you know precisely
who I'm talking about here.
Well, you see,
that's a tough one.
If you're welcoming him back as
an officer who was left behind
in the line of duty, and you
still believe you made the right
decision by doing that,
then all you have to do
is give him a quick pat on
the back and say "well done".
What if... he wasn't
just an officer?
All I know is that I'm
cooking a meal to celebrate
the safe return
of a good friend.
As for what you should do,
I'm afraid that's a question you
need to answer for yourself.
[SAMSON] The way we do things on
Midgrat must be very different
from the things you're
used to as a member
of the royal family.
Royalty must have their own
traditions for you to draw on.
Please forgive me. I shouldn't
have asked the question.
[SAMSON]
I don't mind at all!
I'll treasure this conversation
for the rest of my life!
Not everyone has the
chance to offer an Abh
princess some advice.
Just wait till I tell the
guys back home about this.
They'll never believe me!
Well...!
Jinto...
[MAD WOMAN grunts] What do
you think you're doing?!
It wasn't me! I didn't kill him!
What are you talking about?
Tell me who's been killed!
Ah, your Highness...
I was just about to report
this incident to you.
Y'see... she had this.
[LAFIEL gasps]
Jinto...
How did you get hold of this?
What happened to the
person you got it from?
I already told you I wasn't
the one that killed him!
You mean Jinto...
You mean Count Hyde
has been murdered?!
Look, by the time I got there,
the guy was already
dead, understand?!
What use was he gonna have
for something like that now?
So I took it! Yes, that's right,
I went and took it!
It might not be the
prettiest thing in the world,
but it was a shame to
let it go to waste!
[LAFIEL gasps]
I've ordered my men
to go to the location
where this woman says
she found the body.
If there is a body,
then we can confirm
whether or not
it's the Count.
I'm going with you.
[TOMASOF]
Is this the body?
[MAD WOMAN] Yup. See how he's
lying all twisted on the floor?
He wasn't like that before,
he just ended up like that
when I took the headband!
Can you confirm his DNA?
[CREW C]
Checking it now.
It'll take a couple of minutes
for the results to come through.
[LAFIEL sighs]
Well, I presume that means
this isn't His Excellency?
His name's not Excellency.
I could have told you that!
I know his name's
not Excellency. His name's Jan.
[TOMASOF] You what?!
Why didn't you tell us?!
Oh dear... I must've forgotten!
[laughs]
Oh... my poor Jan!
Who'd have thought
you'd end up like this.
You were a good man at heart,
even if you were
stingy at times.
Please let me keep
the headband.
I want something to
remember him by.
Some sort of little memento!
Please give me Jan's headband!
Please give it
back to me! Please!
[LAFIEL grunts]
Oh... There's no need
to be like that with me.
All right, keep it.
How did this man get ahold
of the Count's headband?
Well, what will you
give me if I tell you?
We could offer
you some food.
Or clothing, jewelry, whatever.
Gimme food! I need
some food so bad.
You see, they keep all
of it for themselves
and we hardly get anything
to eat round here!
Okay. Food. Now tell us!
[gasps]
He was singing a song...
A song?
[MAD WOMAN]
Yeah, it was kinda weird.
We heard this singing and
went to where the sound
was coming from.
That's when we saw him.
The man with the headband.
And you stole it?
[MAD WOMAN] No! But we
could have if we wanted to.
He was so weak.
The singing man wanted to trade
the headband for some food.
Jan still had a bit of food left
and because we were feeling
kinda mellow and
fluffy from the Alkaik
we'd been smoking,
he agreed to the trade.
[TOMASOF] Where was this?
Where did you find him?
You've got to tell us!
That information'll cost ya!
Very well then. As long
as you take us there.
One more question,
and this is most important.
We need to know how long ago
it was that you saw this man
and took his headband.
Well... Maybe it was yesterday,
or maybe it was even a
month ago, or even a year ago.
How am I s'posed to
remember the details?
When?! It can't have
been yesterday!
And it certainly
wasn't a year ago!
So why are you asking me?
You seem to know more than I do!
[laughs]
She's impossible!
Take us there now!
That is if you still
remember where it was...
[MAD WOMAN]
Of course I remember.
It's in the most important
territory here on the island.
It's near my house.
It's such a beautiful house.
Would you like to
come and see it?
I have a request.
Why, yes of course,
your Highness.
I'd appreciate it if
you could make sure
that Jan gets a proper burial.
I'd arrange it myself, but I
don't know the local customs.
Certainly, your Highness.
But why get involved?
Is it only because he provided
the Count with some food to eat?
No. In the Abh Empire, it's
imperative that we show respect
to those with whom
we do business.
That man engaged in a business
transaction with Count Hyde.
Therefore, I would like to show
my respect by providing
a grave and some flowers.
[TOMASOF]
That's very commendable,
but are you sure you can trust
what that woman told us?
They might have stolen
the headband by force.
However, if she's right,
then at least we have some
hope that the Count
might still be alive.
I don't think it's too late to
check out that woman's story.
[sighs]
I agree...
[CREW B]
Hey, anyone got a light?
[CREW A] 2nd squad! We need
you to get to your positions!
7th squad! Get over here! Hurry!
Is everything okay,
your Highness?
I think I want to wait here.
I understand. Yes, I think
that might be best.
You guys come with me!
Don't forget to
bring the stretcher!
[gasps]
[TOMASOF] Your Excellency!
Count Hyde! Are you there?!
[CREW A]
All units search the building!
[CREW MEMBERS]
Yes sir!
[CREW A]
Get a move on!
[CREW MEMBERS]
Yes sir!
[CREW MEMBERS chattering]
Heh... it's perfect! It'll be
the best meal he's ever had!
[EKURYUA]
Huh?
What's the matter,
Second Aviator Ekuryua?
[EKURYUA] I thought... I thought
I just heard something.
What did you hear?
Tell me.
I must've... imagined it.
[LAFIEL slowly breathes]
[TOMASOF]
Your Highness!
--[CREW A] He's still alive!
--[TOMASOF] That's him!
It's the Count!
[LAFIEL]
Jinto!
Jinto... Jinto... Jinto!
[LAFIEL]
Jinto...! Jinto!
[JINTO grunts]
Too bright...
Turn down the lights a bit.
Hey... Lafiel...
Long time no see.
Yes. I'm sorry...
You know what? I think
you've lost some weight.
[JINTO chuckles]
It's always been hard...
For you to say what
you feel inside.
[JINTO coughs]
[JINTO]
Oh...
[LAFIEL]
Let's go home.
Samson has been busy
preparing a meal for you.
I expect the doctor would at
least let you eat some soup.
Ah... That sounds good.
I'll look forward to it.
You know, I was dreaming again.
What were you dreaming about?
It's hard. There were
so many of them.
But I'll try to... In all
of the dreams there was...
Huh?
[grunts]
[LAFIEL]
What did you want to say?
I thought that Abriels...
didn't let themselves cry...
...my precious little Princess.
[LAFIEL gasps]
[LAFIEL]
Idiot...
[SAMSON] Ah! All engines
fully operational.
There we are!
All laser cannons fully
repaired and ready for action.
Looks like we're going
to hand this ship over
in perfect condition to
whoever's taking over from us.
But of course! We've always
made a point of
taking care of this ship,
through thick and thin!
I have to admit I find
it extremely unusual
that not a single officer
is staying on board.
Ekuryua here has
thankfully signed up
to be my navigator
on my next ship.
I don't suppose there's any way
I can persuade you to join us,
Line Wing Aviator?
I'm afraid not.
I've already fulfilled my duty.
I think the time has come for me
to retire and enjoy my pension.
[SOBAASH]
That's a shame.
[SAMSON] I was pretty surprised
to learn that the other two
decided to leave the
Star Forces, though.
You know what, though?
I think they'll change their
minds and come back.
You could be right!
Well, Basroil , a fond farewell.
[JINTO]
Hey! Diaho!
[JINTO] I guess it must be
true that cats have no heart.
He doesn't seem to
remember me at all!
It might have something to
do with the fact that you're
handling him too roughly, Jinto.
You might have a point there!
[LAFIEL] You're not going to
bring him with you, are you?
[JINTO] Why not?
He's my cat, after all.
But don't you think he seems to
have settled down pretty well?
I mean, he might be
happier staying here.
I guess he is more of a
softie than he used to be!
I'm sure his eyes used to have
more of a wild glint about them.
Don't be stupid. They've never
had a wild glint!
Diaho's never been anywhere
close to being wild,
even when he was a kitten!
Even when he was
a kitten? Really?
And who was the one who
raised him, huh? Whoa!
Well, okay. I mean it's not like
we're leaving straight away.
You see, doesn't he
look happy here?
He'll forget all about it
in a couple of days.
Do you think that
white cat's become
his girlfriend or something?
It is a female...
Oh yes, she's quite the lady!
Selkurka, come over here!
If Diaho's coming with us,
then maybe I should
bring her along too.
They seem to like each other.
It's great how they come
when you call them!
Hey Diaho! Come over here!
Come here, kitty!
See? There's still
some wild cat in him!
Maybe he just doesn't
like you very much.
Hey, thanks a lot!
[LAFIEL] So Selkurka,
what do you think?
Do you want to come with me?
We're going to a place called
Martine which is far
away in the Hyde System.
Apparently there's lots
of interesting creatures
living on that planet.
I'm sure there'll be
some that you can chase.
Well, what do you say, Selkurka,
are you coming with us or not?
Listen Lafiel... are you sure
you're doing the right thing?
What do you mean?
I mean leaving
the Star Forces...
...and coming back to
my home with me.
But I thought we'd already
been through all this.
It's going to be fine. If you
count the time I spent training
in the Academy, I've been
in the Star Forces
for about ten years now.
Taking a long vacation's
not going to affect my career.
A vacation? Okay, so a
vacation won't affect
your career in the Star Forces,
but what about you
becoming the next Empress?
[LAFIEL] The current Empress
is from the Cluve Royal Family.
It could still be a couple
of generations before
a member of our family sits on
the throne. It's no big deal.
[JINTO]
But even so...
[LAFIEL] I'm more worried about
what's going to happen to you.
I hated not knowing whether you
were dead or alive. I really...
I really don't want to
go through that again.
Well, thank you
for saying that,
but I'm only going back home.
I'm sure I'm going to be fine.
At least I'm fairly
sure I'll be fine.
Really? I seem to
remember you telling me
you were scared of returning
to the place you were born.
Ha. To tell you the truth,
it is a bit scary.
Look, I know that it's something
I'm going to have to face up to
sooner or later, but it's
got nothing to do with you.
I don't want to get you
involved in something
that's my problem, Lafiel.
[LAFIEL]
Hm. Be honest with me.
Do you want me to go back home
with you or not? Be honest!
Give me a straight answer,
Come on, Count Lin
Syune Locke Hyde!
I... want you...
I can't hear you.
If you agree to be by my side,
I'll be very happy, Lafiel.
[LAFIEL sighs]
Then it's decided!
[JINTO speaking Baronh]
[LAFIEL speaking Baronh]