[COMM. OFFICER]
The enemy fleet is 300 kedrel
away from the Lobnas Gate.
Estimated time of arrival
in this system:
approximately three hours.
[SPOOR] What's the situation
down on the planet?
[KUFADIS] From their latest
report, I'd say they need
another five hours to complete
the evacuation into Plane Space.
So... It seems that
my precious ships
are going to be put in a
dangerous position after all.
All ships! Prepare to depart.
At the Lobnas Gate.
Passing through.
[radio chatter]
[KUFADIS]
All ships of the First Fleet
have safely passed
through the Lobnas Gate.
[COMM. OFFICER] As planned,
we have 11 patrol ships
joining us from
the Altec region.
That means we only have 33 ships
if we include the flagship.
[SPOOR] That's weak for a
reconnaissance squadron,
let alone a battle situation.
Chief of Staff.
I want you to assemble
thirty of the ships into
five temporary formations.
I want the remaining two ships
to be under our direct control.
Roger. Understood.
[SPOOR] I find it hard to
believe that we're actually
putting so much effort
into trying to save
such an insignificant
little system.
I agree. It seems crazy.
[SPOOR] Keep transmitting
the signal to assemble.
[KUFADIS] The ships are now
assembled from numbers
one to five in a
temporary formation.
[COMM. OFFICER]
The enemy fleet are now
less than 200 kedrel away!
They're not running?
[KUFADIS]
Well, I guess they know
they've got a
huge advantage.
[SPOOR] It's so humiliating
knowing we have to fight
when the odds are
stacked against us like this.
[KUFADIS]
I know.
[SPOOR] My, my...
The enemy sure seems calm.
[KUFADIS] They probably don't
understand what's going on.
Ya think so? I know
just how they feel.
[KUFADIS] Here we are
defending the Lobnas Gate,
which has virtually no
strategic importance,
with a fleet that has virtually
no chance of winning...
[SPOOR]
I've got it!
Chief of Staff.
Send a communication
bubble to the enemy fleet!
What do you want me to say?
[SPOOR] That this battle is
pointless for both of us.
I don't think you need
me to tell you why.
It would be irrational for
the enemy fleet to fight.
They wouldn't run the risk of
suffering damage just so they
could arrive in normal space
a couple of hours sooner
than if they waited
for us to leave!
Besides, if they don't
understand the situation here,
they're going to think that
this Star Forces Commander
is stupid! Stupid! Do ya hear?
And I can't bear
the idea of that.
I see where you're going.
If we could just get the
enemy fleet to hold back
for a few hours,
we'd be out of here
and there wouldn't be
any need to fight at all!
[SPOOR] The letter should go...
something like this:
"I am the Supreme Commander
of Operation Hunter
First Fleet, Admiral Spoor.
Our objective is to maintain
a presence in the Lobnas Gate
region for a short time.
It would be pointless
to oppose us.
Therefore remain in your current
position until we have retreated
from the area."
What do you think about that?
It's a good start, but I
think it would be wise
to re-word it here and there.
Really? Well... I think I'll
let you deal with the details.
But we don't have much time!
I'll get onto it straight away.
This is the First Fleet of the
Star Forces Operation Hunter.
We do not wish to
engage in battle.
We promise that we will retreat
from the area in six hours.
Therefore we request that
you refrain from advancing
any further.
The enemy fleet has
stopped advancing.
They've sent back a
communication bubble.
"This is the Salai Sector Fleet
of the United Mankind
Peace Corps.
We will grant you a grace
period of one hour to retreat."
That's all there is.
[SPOOR] If we could
retreat that quickly,
we wouldn't have had to do
this in the first place.
Isn't that obvious to them?
Tell them an hour isn't going
to be long enough for us.
Tell them we need
at least 24 hours.
You can't ask them for 24!
We originally promised them
it would take six hours
for us to retreat!
If everything goes
according to plan,
we can be out of here in five.
But I'd like 12 so I
can have some leeway.
But I thought you just said
to ask for 24 hours, not 12.
[SPOOR] You've never worked
in business, have you,
Chief of Staff?
No, My entire working life I've
been devoted to the Star Forces.
Then it's no wonder
you don't understand.
In the world of trade, no price
is fixed. Not one. Nope.
We're stuck in this situation,
so let's have some fun!
I say we haggle
with our opponent!
Right...
Ask them for 24 hours.
If you say so...
[COMM. OFFICER]
We have a reply. Mm...
"Your original request
was for six hours.
Now you're asking for 24.
Can you explain why?"
End of message.
[SPOOR] Tell them the original
transmission was a mistake.
Make another request for
them to refrain for 24 hours.
This might sound rude, but that
enemy commander is an amateur.
Negotiations take longer
if they waste time
asking dumb questions.
Perhaps they're not used
to doing business this way.
It is a bit unconventional.
And what happens if
they don't give way?
If that happens,
then we have to fight.
Another reply:
"We would like an
explanation as to why
the time you need has
increased fourfold."
When the negotiations
have been finalized,
we'll let them know.
Send that to them.
Their reply:
"We demand to know why you are
being so secretive with us."
Tell them that's a secret.
[COMM. OFFICER] The reply is:
"We do not recognize you
as being a negotiator in
good faith." End of message.
So are they saying they want
to end the negotiations?
Ask them that.
That's too confrontational!
If they say yes,
then we're going to have a
battle on our hands in no time!
The enemy fleet shows
no signs of movement.
I'd say that shows they probably
want to avoid a battle.
But what if worse
comes to worst?
It's sad when an agreement can't
be reached through negotiation.
But if you can overcome that
disappointment, you're well
on your way to becoming a
successful businessman.
This will be a useful
learning experience for you!
I'm in the Star Forces!
I don't want to leave them to
become a businessman!
That's such a shame,
my dear Chief of Staff.
Just think of the fun
you'll be missing out on.
All that haggling.
Ah well, it's your life,
so I suppose I don't have
the right to interfere in it.
But right now I'm the one who's
negotiating with these guys.
So hurry up and send
them my message.
[COMM. OFFICER] Reply:
"We understand your desire
to continue with
the negotiations.
We acknowledge your request
for twenty-four hours grace.
However, we have decided
that you must still retreat
within one hour."
End of message.
[SPOOR] Mm! This enemy
commander's very good.
[SPOOR chuckles]
[KUFADIS] She's enjoying
this little game even more
than if she was
actually fighting.
[SPOOR] This person has
definitely passed my test
as a worthy playmate,
whoever he or she is!
[KUFADIS]
How should we reply?
[SPOOR] Tell them why
we're still here
and why we want more time.
Explain it slowly. Take as
much time as possible.
You could even juice the
story up a bit, if you like.
[KUFADIS] Okay. Where do
you want me to start?
[SPOOR] How about from
when the universe began?
[KUFADIS]
I can't include all that!
[SPOOR]
Lighten up, will you?
Tell them it's impossible
for us to retreat in an hour.
And that we'd be happy to
give them an explanation
of our reasons,
if they so desire.
We've already managed to
delay them for an extra hour
with these questions.
[COMM. OFFICER]
Reply:
"We don't want
your explanations.
We have our own
reasons for wanting you
out of this region, and those
reasons are no concern of yours.
We will wait for two more hours,
after which we will advance
and attack anyone
who stands in our path,
with the intention
of obliteration."
End of message.
Oh well, at least
they're being honest.
The enemy commander is
obviously very dedicated.
A bit like you,
wouldn't you say, my dear?
Mm... Well, I guess we're not
going to get any more time.
Do you think they have
a problem with supplies?
Probably. That would explain
why they don't want to wait.
If they run out, they'd turn
into space-time particles
scattered across the universe!
But they must have some
strength left to fight,
otherwise they wouldn't have
threatened to obliterate us.
Can't we reduce their
strength even more?
Try and extend the negotiations
for as long as possible?
Stop whining, you sound
like a sore loser!
The skill of negotiating
is knowing when to quit.
Um... what message do
you want me to send?
[SPOOR]
Let's see...
"Your message has been
received and understood.
We will do our utmost to
evacuate the area within
two hours but we
may not be successful.
I suggest we suspend further
contact to conserve energy."
Something like that, anyway.
[KUFADIS] How unlike
our Commander in Chief
to issue such a
moderate statement!
[SPOOR] We'd better get ready,
Chief of Staff.
When they attack,
there'll be no mercy.
And we're totally outnumbered.
We have to prepare ourselves
for the worst. The very worst.
How I hate this...
[ LASHKAU CREW A]
Fifteen minutes before the enemy
fleet advances!
[GABORT] This will be the
last trip. Everything depends
on how much time Admiral
Spoor can buy us now.
[LAFIEL]
True.
Commander! We have an airplane
asking for permission to land.
An airplane? Whose is it?
The territorial government's?
[ DARKSES OFFICER d] Yes.
The Territorial Representative
would like to talk
to Her Highness,
the Territorial Ambassador.
My name's Tomasof,
the new Representative.
It's a pleasure to
meet you in person
for the first time, Ambassador.
Are you on your own?
[TOMASOF]
You might want to see this.
Where did you get hold of that?
Well, the rebellion...
let's just say it's
become very disorganized.
[TOMASOF] We thought that in
the chaos, we might be able
to determine where the
Deputy Ambassador
was being held
and rescue him.
So, we contacted
your ship up in orbit.
They scanned the surface of the
planet and thought they had
managed to locate him for us.
[LAFIEL]
No one told me.
[TOMASOF] However, it was
only his Excellency's Clyuno
that they had traced, not the
Deputy Ambassador himself.
So, do you know what
happened to him?
[TOMASOF]
No, I'm afraid not.
That personal communicator
was all we found.
Ma'am, I'm sorry, but we've been
unable to trace his position.
We had no more time
to try and find him.
I see...
You did all you could.
You have my sincere thanks.
[KUFADIS]
It's time.
The enemy fleet has
started to advance!
I love it when people make
their entrance right on cue!
Tell all ships under our
command to prepare for battle!
All ships fire
challenge signals!
You mean we're going to fight?
But of course. There are
still some Imperial ships
that haven't left the
Lobnas System yet.
We managed to buy them
quite a bit of time
with our negotiations.
Don't you think we've
done more than enough
to help them with
their mission already?
That's one way of
looking at it, I suppose.
But we can do more.
Very well, then.
[COMM. OFFICER] The enemy's
frontline squadrons will be
in range of our mobile
space-time mines in ten seconds!
[KUFADIS] The enemy squadrons
have split into two groups:
front and rear!
[SPOOR] It makes me wonder
if the squadrons at the rear
are made up of supply ships.
[KUFADIS] If so, it's a very
obvious formation to use.
[SPOOR]
That's what's worrying me.
COMM. OFFICER]
The enemy's frontline squadrons
are now within range.
[SPOOR]
Hm... They're not firing.
Well, I guess the enemy doesn't
want to waste their mines
if they can help it.
I've got it.
What?
[SPOOR] I want the Fourth and
Fifth squadrons to remain
in their current positions
ready to shoot down
any enemies trying to
sneak through the gate.
Don't let a single ship escape!
The rest of us will attempt to
break our way through the
enemy's front line. Then we
will attack the rear.
Now wait a minute!
Our squadrons are weak enough as
it is without splitting them up!
It'll be like suicide!
What if we can't break through?
We'll be surrounded
and they'll wipe us out!
You listen to me,
Chief of Staff.
Back at home we're gathering
together the artists from all
28 provinces.
Their task is to construct
the Letopanyu family tomb.
Once it is finished, we intend
to hold a great banquet
to celebrate its completion.
It's kind of a
tradition in our family.
[KUFADIS] I can think of
more pleasant traditions.
Okay, but what has your family
tomb got to do with any of this?
The celebration banquet
is planned to take place
in 12 years' time. I'd like
you to be on the guest list.
Uh, thank you,
that'll be a great honor.
But frankly, I can't
think that far ahead.
There's some important
things to sort out here first.
[SPOOR] These Kau class patrol
ships of ours are good ships.
However, they are
mass-produced and functional.
They're certainly not good
enough or beautiful enough
for me to die in. Don't worry.
We're not going to be wiped out.
I won't let that happen.
I've got a plan.
[SPOOR grunts]
All ships, take up the eighth
dense pack formation in
individual space-time bubbles!
Can't the bubbles
at least be arranged
in half-squadron formations?
Absolutely not, Chief of Staff.
I don't have time to
explain my reasons.
Just trust me and do as I say!
But... Commander!
Yes, Commander in Chief.
[KUFADIS With just one ship
in each space-time bubble,
their defenses will be too weak,
even if it means they will have
increased speed as a result.
[KUFADIS You know, up to
this point Admiral Spoor
has always been an excellent
commander in battle.
[KUFADIS sighs] Oh well,
Kufadis Wef Espiel Sespy.
People have to die sometime.
At least if I die in battle,
I'm not going to have to
worry about how I can refuse
her invitation to celebrate
the opening of her tomb!
Only fire mines at the outer
vessels of the enemy formation!
Target the enemy front line!
The enemy doesn't seem
to be firing any mines
as a counter attack!
The rear squadrons are
splitting down the middle!
Send out the
communication ships!
Have them attack the rear
squadron to the right.
We'll take up a half-squadron
space-time bubble formation.
Hurry!
[CREW C]
Kurekuaku . Space-time fusion!
[CREW B]
Doubilge . Space-time fusion!
Fourth Squadron has
received its orders.
[CREW C] We can confirm
that the Fifth squadron
has received its orders.
They're heading to attack the
enemy on the right hand side!
[KUFADIS] The enemy's
frontline squadrons
are starting to attack
from both sides!
Turn the ship around!
We need to target the squadrons
at the rear on the left!
And to do that, we have to break
through the enemy frontline!
Fire mines in all directions!
[ LASHKAU CREW B] All vessels
in the second squadron:
Launch your mines!
We'll stop the enemy
from getting through!
[CREW A] They're surrounding
the first squadron!
[ LASHKAU CREW B] Keep attacking
but stop space-time fusion!
Remember, our target
is the squadron
at the back on the left!
[CREW E] The Loomukau has been
hit! We've got to fix it fast!
We've lost the first squadron
because of that enemy attack!
[CREW B]
This is the Ryuumubilge .
We have encountered space-time
fusion with enemy ships!
Request immediate help!
[ LASHKAU CREW B] Mobile laser
cannon! Attack all ships!
[CREW B]
Sector 18 is on fire!
[sporadic radio chatter]
The Ryuumubilge is in trouble!
They've lost all
battle capabilities!
They want permission
to abort right now!
Permission granted.
So, Chief of Staff,
you know what you've
gotta do here, right?
Yes. Keep our space-time bubbles
ready for an emergency response.
And to make sure that the
ships are always flying
in half-squadron formations.
Excellent. Keep up
the good work!
[COMM. OFFICER]
The Loomukau has exploded!
Now the bridge on the
Sryuzubilge has been
destroyed and they can't
generate a space-time bubble.
There's no response from the
captain or the other officers.
Damn! It exploded as well!
[CREW B] We've got mines coming
in on the right hand side!
[CREW A] The laser cannon
won't get them in time!
[ LASHKAU CREW B]
Emergency mode!
[CREW D] The stern's been hit!
Can you give us a damage report?
[CREW C]
A lot of casualties
and serious damage
to the main engines!
[COMM. OFFICER] The Uzetkau's
engine capability's gone!
They've lost power!
There's only one ship left
in the second squadron.
It's the Suumubilge.
They're requesting permission to
join one of the other squadrons!
[ LASHKAU CREW C]
Explosion on the left!
Prepare for the shockwave!
[COMM. OFFICER] Can you
confirm which ship exploded?
Let's hope it
was an enemy ship!
[COMM. OFFICER]
It was the Kurekukau .
[KUFADIS grunts] Let the
Suumubilge fuse with
our space-time bubble!
[COMM. OFFICER]
Too late.
The Suumubilge
has just exploded!
When are those people going to
escape from the Lobnas System?!
Don't lose your temper
when you're on my bridge,
Chief of Staff!
Uh, I'm sorry, Ma'am.
We all want to know when
that's going to happen,
but until it does,
we have to be patient.
Yes, of course.
[ LASHKAU CREW C] There's been
a direct hit in Sector 13!
There are also pressure
leaks in Sector 15,
but the damage is minimal.
How could we let our
ship get damaged
while bearing the
Flag of Gasarus.
How humiliating...
[KUFADIS] It looks like the
other ships in our fleet
did okay, the enemy's
rear squadron has been
virtually destroyed!
[SPOOR] We might have
succeeded in stopping them
from passing through
the Lobnas Gate.
[KUFADIS] True. But we
only have six ships left.
Well, I guess that's it.
We can't last much longer.
All ships retreat!
But that's impossible!
The enemy is blocking our
path in every direction!
[SPOOR]
Stop worrying, Chief of Staff.
This battle is
completely pointless.
At least it's pointless for
those of us who couldn't
negotiate enough time
to get those wretched
transport ships out of
the Lobnas System.
As soon as they see that our
ships are beginning to retreat,
the enemy themselves
will realize
this battle is pointless.
There's no way
they'll come after us.
Unless, of course,
they're completely stupid,
in which case it'll be
a different story.
It's a possibility.
[SPOOR]
Turn the ship around.
We'll head for the center
of the Milky Way Gates.
I don't care what they think,
we're gonna retreat
whether they like it or not!
Squadron space-time bubble,
complete the maneuver!
[ALL crew]
Roger!
[ LASHKAU CREW B]
All ships! Follow the Lashkau !
[COMM. OFFICER
The enemy's coming after us!
Distance 10 sheskedrel.
Space-time fusion!
Two more enemy ships
at 170 degrees!
Looks like the enemy is stupid!
Oh! Can they really
hate me that much?
Do what you can
to break through!
[sporadic radio chatter]
[grunts]
The Doubilge has just exploded.
[SPOOR grunts]
What have I gone and done?
Did I misjudge the
right time to retreat?
Your Highness, the boarding
of the transport ships
is now complete.
[LAFIEL] Huh? Right.
All ships take off immediately.
[GABORT] Roger. We'll join
the fleet in orbit
and head straight for
the Lobnas Gate.
This is the captain speaking.
All ships prepare for
emergency take off.
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Commence gravitational control.
Prepare for take off.
Gravitational control is now on!
[GABORT]
Ready for take off?
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Ready!
[LAFIEL]
Jinto...
[softly grunts]
Huh?
[JINTO gasps]
Dokufu!
[gasps]
[JINTO]
Emergency take-off position?
It's the last ship... Oh, no!
[JINTO] I can't afford to die,
not in a place like this.
[DARKSES OFFICER C]
Commence countdown to take-off.
T-minus 20 seconds!
[ANGUS yells]
[ANGUS]
Damn the Abh!
I won't let you take my women!
Angus...
[ DARKSES OFFICER C] Five...
Four... Three... Two... One...
Lift off!
No! What about my children?!
My children!
No...! No...!
[grunts]
[LAFIEL]
If you'd died back there,
I would have been
sorry that you'd gone.
[JINTO]
Lafiel... I will see you again.
[GABORT]
What's the situation?
[ DARKSES OFFICER D]
Checking now.
We have a response!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
The enemy fleet's passing
through the Lobnas Gate!
It looks like we didn't make it.
What should we do now?
[LAFIEL] We have no other
choice but to go through.
All ships activate their
space-time bubble generators!
All ships prepare space-time
bubble generators... Activate!
[ DARKSES OFFICER D]
Space-time bubble activated!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
The enemy's right behind us!
Okay, here they come!
Prepare for battle.
The laser cannon is ready.
Let's catch up with
the transport ships
and get out of here!
[ DARKSES OFFICER C]
Enemy ships confirmed ahead!
[LAFIEL]
Ignore them and keep moving!
[SAMSON] Is this really all
that's left of the First Fleet?
[LAFIEL] Perhaps I'm not fit
to be a military officer.
I mean... I know it
was my decision
that we got involved in this
mess in the first place.
The Vascotton Gate?
So, now we've come full circle.
[DUBUS] There are some
people who enjoy it.
And I wish you all
the best, Admiral.
[EKURYUA]
He was the first human I met
who was about my age.