[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
Hey guys, this isn't
the right road!
Did you input the wrong route?
[PRISON GUARD T]
Hey, what's going on?
Huh?
Damn! I can't seem to
over-ride the program!
[PRISON GUARD U] It's useless.
I've secured the system.
[grunts]
How could you...?
[chuckles]
Everything's been taken care of.
[JINTO grunts] I don't
understand why you guards
want to aid the prisoners
with this rebellion.
Ha! That's easy. It's for
the Alkaik of course.
And what's that? The name
of some sort of god?
I suppose for some
of the people here,
it really is like
a god to them.
It's a narcotic only
found on Lobnas II.
They're doing this for drugs?!
Yes. We don't know who
started it, but the prisoners
have been manufacturing drugs
using a very primitive method
of extraction from
the Alkaik plant.
And now the prison guards
have started to infiltrate
the drug trade?
Yes, that's right.
[PRISON GUARD 18U]
[PRISON GUARD 18T]
Hey! Don't be stupid!
Give me the gun!
Argh... Come on...
[PRISON GUARD U]
No!
Ha!
No, stop!
[grunts]
Why do you have
to be so cruel?
I thought you two were friends?
Some things are more
important than friendship
in this life.
I hope you understand now...
...why I didn't want you to
withdraw even temporarily.
If we were to leave them alone
for two months, then this
planet would be quickly be
taken over by drug addicts.
And this place would
turn into a living hell.
Why didn't you tell
me all this earlier?
I didn't want to show
any weakness to an enemy!
[PRISON GUARD U]
Administrative Director.
Don't you want to know
what's going to happen next?
I mean aren't you curious to
know what I've planned?
About what I'm going to do with
you and your friend here?
I know that you're a coward
and therefore I know
you're not going to do
anything with us that might
jeopardize your access
to the supply of Alkaik.
I also know that scum like you
don't work for themselves,
so my guess is that you're under
orders to take us directly
to Angus or Dokufu.
[whistles]
Very clever, Director.
Absolutely right. You need
intelligence to become
a high-ranking official
in the United Mankind.
[ALL grunt]
How come this
isn't bulletproof?
I didn't think I'd need it!
Hey! We've gotta go back!
[PRISON GUARD U]
I can't go back now! Ha, ha.
Your Excellency, surely you've
got some sort of weapon?
I never thought
that I'd need it.
I still can't believe
they took over the
Administrative Agency
so quickly!
[PRISON GUARD U] I've kidnapped
the Administrative Director.
Take me to the boss.
He's expecting me.
[JINTO sighs] I don't think
that they'll want me here.
Do you realize what you've done?
Why did you have to
bring him along as well?!
[PRISON GUARD U] I'm sorry sir,
but I didn't have much choice.
He was there,
so I had to bring him.
[ANGUS]
It's okay.
So we've got more hostages...
[DOKUFU]
Are you crazy? Don't you see?
This could cause a major
incident with the Empire!
Us going and kidnapping
the Administrative Director
is one thing, but a
nobleman from the Empire
is a completely
different matter!
If that's what you think,
then you should let
his Excellency go.
And you should let me go too,
although somehow I doubt
that's going to happen.
You're absolutely right. Ha!
Releasing a mere
Administrative Director
will accomplish nothing.
Of course, we might change our
minds if you decide to cancel
that emigration permit of yours.
I'd never do that!
It's not negotiable!
[ANGUS]
Do you like children?
[MEIDEEN] Why the sudden
change of subject?
Yes, I love them. So what
exactly is your point?
[ANGUS]
I love children.
I have five of my own
scattered all around.
But I'm not allowed
to see any of them.
So that's why I
want another child.
And if all the women leave,
that's not gonna be possible.
You mean all this
is just for that?!
Whaddya mean "just for that"?!
[DOKUFU] Hey, hey, hey!
Just cool it, would you?
Can't you see it from
his point of view?
He simply has a dream of being
the head of a happy family!
You won't get any
sympathy from me!
If you'd lived a decent
lifestyle, no one would've
taken your children from
you in the first place!
And besides, what about
the children of the people
you've killed? They'll never
see their fathers again!
We have no interest in
remembering the past.
What we're interested
in is the future.
A future where our
children can run free
across the land on Lobnas II.
And you're taking that
opportunity away from us!
[JINTO]
Excuse me. If you remember,
we could always provide you with
artificial birth technology.
Why is it so difficult
for you to understand?
A child needs a mother!
No matter how much love a father
thinks he can give his child,
it's not enough. There's always
a barrier between them.
But the love of a mother
is unconditional,
something children
intuitively recognize.
But half the Abh race
doesn't have a mother
and they seem to
be perfectly fine!
Yeah? Well maybe that explains
why you're all so screwed up!
[DOKUFU]
I'm sorry, your Excellency.
We have no intention of using
any artificial birth technology
from you or anyone else.
Have I made myself clear to you?
[MEIDEEN] In that case you
might as well forget about
having children altogether.
Because you don't have a choice
between artificial means
and natural means.
Your choice is to use the
artificial birth technology,
or look to a future
without any children at all!
[DOKUFU] So you have no
intention of canceling
the emigration order?
No way!
[DOKUFU] Well, if you're
not going to cancel it...
I am a high-ranking official
of the United Mankind
and I refuse to give in to
such threatening behavior!
I'll just have to
kill him, then.
Huh? Why me?!
What do you think you would
achieve by killing him?
You said yourself that
you don't want to cause
a major incident
with the Empire!
Killing him will mean
huge repercussions!
[DOKUFU] No one needs to
know that I was the one
who killed him. It's easy
to get lost on Lobnas II.
He could just happen
to "disappear"!
Along with the Administrative
Director, of course.
[MEIDEEN]
But what good would that do?
You're going to end up putting
yourself in an even worse
position than
you're in right now!
[DOKUFU] So will the former
residents of Lobnas II
who've already left the planet.
I haven't the slightest
idea what'll happen,
but we intend to
enjoy ourselves.
The emigration process
will be cancelled.
You can't do that!
Look, whatever you
decide to do to us,
you're gonna have to
pay for it in the end!
[DOKUFU]
Don't worry.
We're confident that one day
we're going to see lots
of little children
running around here!
[gasps]
Ha! Make up your mind!
I won't do it!
[chuckles]
[DOKUFU sighs] I don't think
I can bring myself to do it.
[ANGUS] Huh? Why didn't
you kill the coward?!
Because he's part of
the nobility. The Empire
would come down like a ton
of bricks if we killed him.
It's far too dangerous for us.
However...
There's nothing to stop me
from killing you, is there?!
You go ahead. If you kill me,
then you've got a big problem
to deal with. You won't be able
to cancel the emigration order.
As the new
Territorial Representative,
I'll cancel the order.
[MEIDEEN] I'm afraid
that's impossible.
I've already given the
Territorial Ambassador
a list of who should succeed
me in case of emergencies.
Everyone on that list
is due to emigrate,
but as long as they
remain on this planet,
then the position of Territorial
Representative is taken.
You don't stand a chance
until every person
on the list has left.
Ha, ha. Would I be correct in
assuming that the first person
on the list would be
someone like Tomasof?
[MEIDEEN gasps]
I can see right through you,
Director. Well, is it Tomasof?
It doesn't matter whose
names are on the list.
Ah, but you see it does matter.
Surely you didn't think that
he's the only one who's
moved over to our side?
No. I'm sure there're
many more like him.
But Tomasof would never
have anything to do
with the Alkaik drug trade.
So... Tomasof's name
is on the list!
[MEIDEEN]
Suit yourself.
[DOKUFU] That's exactly
what I intend to do.
Are you sure you won't give the
order to cancel the emigration?
Of course I won't!
Then you're not needed anymore.
Don't do it...
[DOKUFU] Cancel the order and
this trigger won't get pulled.
[MEIDEEN] No! There's no
way I can do that!
Huh? I should have
realized this before.
Tomasof can't
be on your side.
If he was, then you would have
known already that he could
cancel the emigration order
and you wouldn't have had
any hesitation in killing me!
[DOKUFU] You may find this
difficult to believe,
but I really dislike
having to kill people.
That's why I'm giving
you so many chances.
That's all there is to it.
Frankly, your friend
Tomasof will do
whatever I tell him to do.
Of course, you could save us
all a lot of time and trouble
if you just went ahead and
canceled the order yourself.
It seems like the
simplest solution to me.
I have no intention of doing so.
Tomasof would never betray me
and you're lying if
you say otherwise.
You're nothing but a
third rate con man!
How about I give you five more
seconds to make up your mind.
Five... Four...
Three... Two... One...
Time's up.
[JINTO grunts]
[JINTO]
Huh?
[grunts]
I thought this guy was
meant to be a soldier.
[DOKUFU]
He's one of those soldiers
drawn from the nobility.
He's probably never even
seen a dead body before.
Why did you do that?
I may have not
liked him very much,
but at heart he was a good,
responsible person.
Why did you have to
go and kill him?!
This rebellion is a
different kind of war,
your Imperial Highness!
Even the Empire kills
huge numbers of good
and responsible people
when they are at war.
How can you criticize
us for this?!
That may be true but...
That may be true but I...
[chuckles] Now what do we
have next on our agenda?
You should go and
contact Tomasof.
Well, well. I must have
been very convincing
if you believed what
I said about him!
[JINTO]
Huh?
[DOKUFU] A do-gooder like him
would never have anything
to do with drugs.
Although, we shouldn't
underestimate him as
one of our enemies.
You tricked me, didn't you?!
I didn't trick you!
It was the Administrative
Director who got tricked!
It would've been so
boring for him to die
believing his wishes would be
carried out by his own men.
That's a despicable
thing to do, Dokufu!
[JINTO]
He's right about that!
You should show some respect
for the dead, do you hear me?
We may not have
liked him very much,
but you have to admit
that guy had guts.
[PRISONERS]
Huh?
Anyway, back to business.
We've got to decide
what we'll do next.
Well, now we've got ourselves
stuck with this extra hostage.
The little coward.
Although hostages
who are cowards
can be easier to deal with.
I've already told you:
we can't afford to incur
the wrath of the Empire.
No doubt we'll end up having
to send this "nobleman" home.
I'm sure he'll be upset at the
inconvenience we've put him to,
but he'll soon forget about
a tiny incident like this
on such an unimportant planet.
I'll never forget.
Do you think so?
I don't think I'd ever forget
having a gun held to my head.
Imagine what an impression it
would make on a coward like him!
Whether he remembers or not,
we've gotta work out how to stop
this situation from
getting any worse.
[ANGUS]
Then do something about it.
But... That's easy
enough for you to say.
You see I...
You see, we really don't want
the Empire to get involved
in all this, but if we were
to actively threaten you,
could you put a stop
to the emigration process?
I'm only the Territorial
Deputy Ambassador.
I have no authority.
But you could say a few
words to help me become
the new Territorial
Representative?
I'm only the Territorial
Deputy Ambassador.
I have no authority.
Oh dear... now we're
in big trouble!
So who does have the authority?
[JINTO] Her Highness
the Ambassador, of course.
But she's up in orbit right now.
In that case, we threaten her
and we use him as a hostage.
But it's far too risky!
[ANGUS]
If you can't do it,
then you're as much
of a coward as him.
If my late mother found out I'd
joined forces with such a wimp,
I wouldn't dare
look her in the eye.
I'd sooner kill you first.
[beeping]
Captain! It's the next
Territorial Representative.
Don't connect it.
--[beeping]
--[EKURYUA] Huh?
Now Supply Officer Lin
is trying to get through.
[LAFIEL]
Hm? Okay, put him on.
[EKURYUA]
He's using his Clyuno.
[DOKUFU] Is that the
Territorial Ambassador?
Who am I talking to?
[DOKUFU] I am the newly
inaugurated Prime Minister
of the Lobnas System,
Yuuri Dokufu.
Please, can I talk to you
by regular transmission?
This Clyuno is difficult to use,
although it's a very handy size.
Uh, Captain, it's the next
Territorial Representative.
Go ahead then.
I want to hear your explanation.
If by an explanation, you mean
you want to know why I am in
possession of the Territorial
Deputy Ambassador's Clyuno...
Well, you see, to put it simply,
we've kidnapped him.
[LAFIEL] Hm? Tell me
the truth. Is he alive?
[DOKUFU]
Well, of course.
See for yourself.
Hi...
[LAFIEL]
Why am I not surprised, Jinto?
Now listen to our demands.
I refuse!
Will you at least
listen to them?
After all, we do have
his Excellency,
the Deputy Ambassador,
in our custody.
I demand you to return
him to us. Immediately.
Well, I suppose that may
be the best solution.
[ANGUS]
No! Keep negotiating, Dokufu.
Do you mean to say
you're not the leader?
I want to speak directly
to whoever is in charge.
Well, technically I'm
in charge here.
At least I try my best to be.
[ANGUS] I have never worked
under your command, Dokufu!
Captain, we've analyzed
the voiceprint and we have
a positive identification.
It's Angus, Representative of
the Eastern Detention Sector.
He's been in communication
with us once before.
[ANGUS] We'll never return
this coward to you!
Not as long as you continue to
take the women off this planet!
Jinto is not a coward!
[ANGUS]
Oh yes he is.
He was even frightened at
the sight of a dead body!
Something important has happened
here that you should know about.
These guys have gone
and murdered Meideen!
You must consult the list
and find out who the next
Representative should be!
[ANGUS]
You shut up!
[LAFIEL gasps]
You'll pay for that!
[LAFIEL] I'd like to go down
to that planet right now
and with my bare hands teach
that creep exactly how those
of us who are the kin of the
stars like to exact our revenge.
Do what you want to.
I'm not afraid of dying.
If we can't breed children,
then we might as well be dead.
So stop removing the
women from this planet.
Otherwise we're gonna kill him.
No women, no Deputy-Ambassador.
No matter what you do to us.
Even if you somehow manage
to kill us, you'll never
get him back alive.
Kill you? Don't make me laugh!
Death would be far too
sympathetic a fate!
What do you mean by that?
[SOBAASH]
Well...
Perhaps I can enlighten you,
Mr. Angus, Mr. Dokufu.
You see, we believe that the
faithful execution of revenge...
...is one of the primary reasons
that we, as Abh, exist.
If anyone is found guilty of
unjustly causing the death
of a fellow Abh, we believe
it is critical for them
to learn through experience
that there is a fate far worse
than death in this galaxy.
I believe you Angus,
when you tell us that
you're not afraid to die.
But in what form do you
visualize that death?
If you're expecting death at our
hands to consist of a bullet
from a gun or some sort
of lethal laser beam,
I'm afraid your expectations
are sorely lacking.
I guarantee you will be given
plenty of chances to recognize
just how wrong your
expectations were.
Yes, once you have learned
exactly how the Abh exact
their revenge, you will be
begging and pleading with us
to give you the most painful
death imaginable to mankind.
However, we don't intend
to give you that luxury.
We may not believe
in any religion,
but we do believe in
the existence of hell.
That's because in this galaxy
hell does exist and we know
that for certain, because was
created it and we control it.
You shall experience
first hand the wrath
of the legendary
Emperor Dougnaa.
You shall see how the darkness
of science can be used
to create the
darkness of the soul.
[DOKUFU grunts] Now just
wait a minute, will you?!
In the end, revenge produces
nothing but hatred!
That hatred fuels more hatred,
and revenge continues
in an endless cycle!
[SOBAASH]
That may or may not be true,
but what I do know is that our
reputation for revenge has
been an effective deterrent
against our enemies.
When I was younger,
I traveled a great deal,
visiting strange lands
and encountering many
dangerous situations. I believe
the reason I'm still alive
is that our notoriety kept
me safer than any armor
I could use.
I sincerely hope the
same will be true
in this situation, Dokufu.
For both our sakes...
[DOKUFU]
Huh?
[ANGUS]
No way!
I believe in God!
And before I get thrown
into the hell He created,
it'll be good practice for me
to experience this fake hell
you've dreamt up.
My mind is made up.
If you take the women,
we'll take his life.
All right then.
But promise me something.
Promise me you won't
run away and die
before we can get to you...
[DOKUFU] I really don't
agree with this, you know.
[ANGUS] You're a bigger
coward than any of them!
[SOBAASH]
That's too bad.
But if you change your mind,
please contact us again.
[DOKUFU] Please wait!
I'm against this!
Please listen to me!
You've got to believe that I
wanted to send him back to you!
Oh... Jinto...
[LAFIEL] I am an Abriel
and Abriels don't cry.
I wish I wasn't an
Abriel right now!
[EKURYUA]
Captain!
There's a transmission coming
through from the Lweyses .
It's Line Wing Aviator Samson.
[LAFIEL]
Put him through.
[SAMSON] I'm sorry, Captain.
I should've gone with him.
[LAFIEL]
It's not your fault.
He was the one who
made the decision.
[SAMSON]
Yes, but...
[LAFIEL]
It's all right.
It's his own fault that he was
captured, and it's my fault
that I'm leaving him down there.
[SAMSON]
You intend to abandon him?!
I wanted to speak with you
expecting to receive orders to
head straight back down to the
planet to try and rescue him!
[LAFIEL]
Come back to the ship.
You're not equipped
for a ground battle.
[SAMSON] But Captain! They have
no intention of waging a battle
against the Star Forces.
It would be unthinkable for them
to launch an attack against us!
[LAFIEL]
Return to your original duties.
[SAMSON]
Captain, please.
Allow me to fulfill my
responsibilities to him.
Tell you what. I won't take
my men, I'll go on my own.
My guess is that they
really want to avoid
getting into a fight with us.
All we need to do is provide
them with an opportunity
to give him back.
They've failed and they know it.
But the thing about people
who've failed is they
don't like to admit it.
That's honestly how it
is down there, Captain.
My going there will give them
a chance to return the boy
without losing face
about their failure.
It's a gamble, but please
give me this one chance!
Be silent! I don't want
to hear any more talk
from you about rescuing him.
You're not
responsible here, I am!
Please be quiet,
Samson Bolge Tilsal Tiluse!
Otherwise I'll forget about him.
[ANGUS] Well now we have a
reason for holding him captive
as a hostage, don't we?
[DOKUFU] I said, "Let go of
the Deputy Ambassador!"
[ginshot]
[SPOOR]
Please explain...
But we Spoors can
see through it all.
Would you? Your Highness?
[LAFIEL] That's the first
time she's ever called me
"Your Highness".