[SATOU] Apparently,
skills aren't the only things
that're easy to come by here.
Titles are, too.
[SATOU]
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, yeah, by the way: I wouldn't
look down if I were you.
[ZENA]
Huh? Huh?!
Ah!
[SATOU]
I warned you.
Let's get outta here.
[ZENA]
Thank you for the catch.
I don't remember much.
Only the wyvern
swooping down on me.
I was working my way up
that cliff when, out of nowhere,
you just came flying
down from the sky.
Well, I'm glad you were there.
I'm pretty sure you
just saved my life.
[SATOU]
If I were a younger man,
I'd be head over heels
in love right about now.
Oh, by the way, my name's Satou.
Yes, well.
It's so nice to meet you.
[SATOU]
That was dumb.
I should've asked her
for her name first.
Forgive me, my name's Zena.
I'm 17 and I'm a military mage
on retainer of Count Seiryuu.
I've served in the
territorial army for two years.
I'm not yet married.
Uh. No boyfriend either.
[SATOU] Uh... Where I come
from, that's called TMI.
Stop right there, scum!
Move away from the girl!
[ZENA]
No, Lilio!
Don't hurt him!
He's all right!
We're trying to
save your life, Zena!
Oh. You don't have
anything to fear from me.
I'm just a traveling merchant.
The name's Satou.
A merchant with zero goods?
Sounds fishy.
[SATOU]
She's right.
What sort of a traveling
merchant carries his wares
in a satchel like this?
This is sort of embarrassing but
when that big meteor shower hit,
my packhorse got
spooked and took off.
[SATOU]
I don't really want that skill.
Do you mean the starfall?
That might scare a horse.
But if you'd seen it hit.
You wouldn't be
standing here right now.
You would've run the other way.
The man who saved
my grandfather's life?
He's buried in a grave
near Warrior's Fort.
I journeyed there
to pay my respects.
The starfall happened
when I first arrived.
My horse ran this way.
Show me your papers right now.
You don't need those!
Rules are rules.
Thing is...
I left my papers inside
the pocket of a coat
on the back of my packhorse.
I have nothing to
show you, ma'am.
[IONA sighs]
Very well.
We'll issue new papers
in Seiryuu City.
[SATOU] Maxing out my
trickery and persuasion skills
really did the trick.
I feel so dirty.
[ZENA] And so, shortly
after the starfall's impact,
we were dispatched from
Seiryuu City to the area
where you ended up finding us.
Our orders were to assess
any potential damage.
[SATOU]
A wyvern corpse?
[ZENA] Wyvern hides are tough,
so they make for sturdy armor.
We can usually sell
it for a decent profit.
Yes, that's very true.
Good armor, but bad food.
Really bad.
It's cheap, though.
Sometimes they force us
to eat wyvern to save coin.
Does it taste pretty bad?
It tastes like dirt, kid.
First time I put that
garbage in my mouth,
I spit it right
back in the bowl!
Of course, the slaves in
West Town don't complain
about wyvern meat or any other
kinda food, they'll eat it all.
[SATOU] I didn't realize
they have slaves here.
I sure hope they don't feed me
wyvern when we get to town.
Approximately 80 percent
of Seiryuu City's residents
are full citizens.
The other 20 percent are slaves.
And they're not all human.
[SATOU]
Huh... Cool. There's an elf.
Oh, and some sort
of magical being.
[ZENA]
Look, Satou.
The city's straight ahead!
I meant to ask you.
Do you have somewhere
to stay in town,
or are you in need of
proper accommodations?
Actually, I was thinking about
getting a room somewhere.
In that case, I'd recommend
you try the Gate Inn.
It's just past the main
entrance, on the right side.
A touch pricey,
but it's known far and wide
for its extraordinary cuisine.
[ZENA]
I wish I could stay.
I'm required to
give a debriefing,
so I'm afraid
I have to be going.
I'll stop by later
to say thank you.
[SATOU] Don't worry, you don't
need to thank me at all.
Satou! I'm a member
of the Marientail family.
I have a duty to show
my appreciation!
[SATOU] Jeez, she doesn't take
no for an answer, does she?
I'll see you soon!
[SATOU]
I might be reading into it,
but I totally think
she's in love with me.
[chuckles]
So! How can I help you, Iona?
We owe this man our thanks
for saving Zena's life.
He's lost his papers,
and if you don't mind,
I would like you
to reissue them.
[THORN]
Of course.
The Yamato Stone?
[IONA]
Yes.
Thank you.
Well, young man.
Place both of your hands
on the Yamato Stone, please.
[SATOU]
Yamato Stone?
Should be interesting.
I'm required to ask this.
Are you now, or have
you ever been in the past,
a fugitive from the law?
Oh. No, sir.
State your name, please.
[SATOU]
My name...
I guess my real name
isn't going to fly here.
Satou.
[SATOU]
Uh. My user profile!
Looks like this
is the information
from before I leveled up.
This just gets weirder
and weirder.
All right, kid.
You can take your off hands now.
So, you're a grown up, eh?
I thought you were
a lot younger.
In any case, you're an adult
and you're level one.
Guess your parents never
let you outta the house.
No, they really didn't.
They consider
15 an "adult" here?
[THORN]
Done.
Here.
Try not to lose it again.
You owe me one silver coin.
[SATOU]
Sure.
[THORN]
That's not all.
City entrance tax
is one copper, kiddo.
But, this young man
saved Zena's life.
We can forgive the tax just
this once, don't you think?
Why not?
Don't forget this:
It's your city entry visa.
It's valid for ten days.
If you'd like to
stay in town longer...
...you'll have to request an
extension here at this station
or in Central at town hall.
It'll cost ya three copper
no matter where you go.
[SATOU]
Thanks.
One more thing.
If one of our guards catches
you with an expired visa,
you're gonna owe
a fine of one silver.
If you can't pay,
you'll be made into a slave,
so if I were you,
I'd watch out, kid.
[SATOU]
Right.
Thank you so much, sir.
[SATOU] A life of bondage
'cause you overstay your visa?
Harsh.
[IONA]
Do you see that yellow sign?
That's the Gate Inn; the place
I was telling you about.
Thanks a lot for your help.
Great to meet you, Iona.
I'll see you around!
This townscape is
so freakin' cool.
As a nerd who's devoted
his entire life to creating
new worlds inside a computer,
I have a total dork
boner right now.
[MARTHA]
You there!
You just came in from
outside the front gate, right?
If you need a room,
then you should stay with us!
We'll give you a stellar deal!
Our rooms are clean
and comfortable,
and plus our food's
the best in town by far!
[SATOU]
Who's she?
Thirteen?
For a 13 year old
she is very mature.
The yellow sign.
This is the place.
[MARTHA]
Guess what, Mom?
I brought a customer!
Darling, did you force
him to come here?
Oh no, she didn't at all, ma'am.
I could get used to this.
[MARTHA]
Mom! I wasn't pushy...
[SATOU]
And this lady innkeeper?
I'm gonna be honest:
It's been a while for me,
but she's looking
pretty hot herself.
Uh. Pardon me.
Do you have any luggage, sir?
Oh, uh... Thing is...
I lost all my belongings
when my packhorse ran away
on account of the starfall.
Lucky for me,
I still have my wallet,
otherwise I'd be in
big trouble right now.
That must've been
really tough on you.
For one copper a night you
get a nice room to yourself.
Meals cost extra,
but it is worth the price,
you get a free item per meal.
In that case,
I'll stay ten nights.
Perfect.
That'll be two silvers
on the dot.
[SATOU]
I see.
That means five large
coppers equal one silver.
Ma'am?
Could I get something
to eat right now?
Sorry, we've already put
the fire out in the kitchen.
I do have some leftover
quiche from this morning,
is that all right?
[SATOU]
Great! I'll take that, then.
[MOSA]
Bon appetit!
That'll be one copper, sir.
The dish is our gift.
Mom's quiche is always good,
but it's much tastier
when it's still fresh.
Martha, dear.
Have you cleaned the room
of those cowardly merchants?
They left several hours ago.
Sorry, I haven't.
See you later, Satou!
[SATOU]
Cowardly merchants?
Yes.
They were not
the bravest of men.
When the starfall hit,
the merchants panicked
and started screaming
all sorts of insanities!
"The Demon Lord is
fighting the dragons!"
So, there's a Demon Lord?
Well, there was, long ago.
It's been about 60 or 70 years
now since a hero defeated him.
It's possible he's revived
in another country,
but as of yet, I have not
heard a word about it.
[SATOU]
Hope he doesn't come back.
Demon Lords suck.
I'm glad the hero took him out.
If this works like a game,
then the Demon will revive
as the main character
progresses through the world.
But even if the Demon Lord
does rear his head,
he'll attack Labyrinth City
before here.
That's at the opposite
end of the country.
[SATOU chuckles]
This conversation is
totally freaking me out.
In this part of the world,
wyverns are a
much bigger threat.
Do ya have issues with
dragons around here?
[MOSA] You hear
about them in legends,
but dragons aren't a
problem in these parts.
They're asleep in
the Valley of Dragons,
so we rarely see them.
The last one we saw
was over two years ago.
And the time before that?
Well, was long
before I was born.
A black dragon
attacked back then.
It ate all the sheep and goats;
put the whole community at risk.
[SATOU] Why is she talkin'
about freakin' livestock?
I'm worried about
human casualties.
[PATRON]
Innkeeper! A moment please!
[MOSA]
I'm coming!
Hello, sir!
[SATOU]
Welp, we're done talking.
In that case,
time to dig in.
The main dish is quiche
with a whole lotta potato.
It's cold.
But it's really delicious,
nonetheless.
[SATOU] I thought this was bok
choy, but it's actually cabbage.
[SATOU] Reminds me
of the sauerkraut I ate
when I went on that
super-cheap trip to Germany.
[MARTHA]
Tasty, right?
I told ya the
food's really good.
Uh, hey, you're back.
Are you finished
with your chores?
[MARTHA]
Yep.
I meant to ask.
Is there a place close
to here that sells supplies?
[MARTHA]
Supplies, huh?
Hmm...
You can purchase some
used items and old clothes
from the booths
over on West Street.
New clothes always
cost an arm and a leg,
but if that's your fancy,
go see a tailor at one of
the shops on Central Street.
I was thinking pre-fab.
You know, clothes that
have already been made.
[MARTHA]
Hmm?
Oh! Ready-tailored clothes!
I don't think I've
heard a person
use the term "pre-fab" before.
There're some shops
on Tepta Street,
but they're not cheap either.
[SATOU]
Tepta Street.
[MARTHA]
Oh, I know!
I can take you there!
[MALE VILLAGER A]
So how much?
[FEMALE VILLAGER A]
Two bits per item.
[MALE VILLAGER A]
Two bits?
Too much!
[SATOU] Looks like it's
normal to haggle here.
Whoa!
That must be a demi-human.
[MALE VILLAGER B]
Damn you, you filthy animal!
Stay away from East Town,
do I make myself clear?
You slaves don't deserve
to breath my air.
Do you need something, sir?
[MALE VILLAGER B]
Hah! Are these slaves yours?
Well, put 'em on a leash and
keep 'em in back West Town
where they belong.
Hey, are you all right?
Here. Take it.
Aww!
Thank you.
Bless you.
There's a lotta people
in the streets today,
so you be careful.
[chuckles]
What's the matter?
It's just that you
were being so nice
to those two demi-humans.
Are demi-humans widely
hated in these parts?
[MARTHA]
Mm-hmm.
A long time ago, when hunters
and farmers would come
to the city to make an honest
living selling their crops,
the demi-humans
would murder them.
[SATOU]
Huuuh...
I guess that means
they're thieves and bandits.
Ah! Satou, look!
There's something
I want you to see.
You're going to love this!
[SATOU]
She changes gears fast.
If you want it,
it's yours for four copper.
That's two coppers
too much, friend.
These items are really
expensive to make, friend.
I need at least three.
How 'bout two copper
and two bits?
Two copper and four bits
is the floor for me, pal.
Two copper and three bits
or I'm walking away.
You got a deal!
[MARTHA chuckles]
Thanks so much
for the barrette.
Of course.
And thank you for
showing me around.
If I wanted to win her over,
this would be the perfect moment
to shower her with compliments.
[SATOU]
Whoa!
They call this a dragon mask!
We wear them during
the Harvest Festival.
[FEMALE VILLAGER B]
So what's it gonna be?
The dragon mask will
bring you good health
and a safe home, too.
[SATOU]
Oh...
Do you wear the wig
with the dragon mask?
If you're a dragon,
you wear the mask.
The black wig is for people
who want to play
the part of the brave hero.
The gold wig's a
whole different thing.
It's for people who
fancy themselves
the hero's damsel in distress.
[SATOU] I couldn't make up my
mind, so I decided to splurge:
I got a mask and a wig.
With a title like that,
I'm guessing she doesn't
have many friends.
Hmm? What?
Nothing, I'm fine.
[YUNI hums]
Huh?
Martha!
You're back!
Come meet our guest!
Yuni, this is Satou.
He'll be staying
with us for a while.
Yes, I know, I've already
prepared him a nice room.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, Satou.
For your trouble.
Thank you very much!
[SATOU]
Good to know. Tips are normal.
Oh. Almost forgot.
Are there baths here?
Well, there's a public
bath in the inner-walls,
but unfortunately, commoners
like us are not allowed there.
[SATOU] Ah. What do you
usually do, Martha?
There's a well right out back,
typically I just
wash myself there.
Well, I guess that's that, then!
I'll have whatever you
recommend for dinner, Martha.
All right.
Would you like
something strong to drink
to go with your tasty meal?
[SATOU]
Not strong.
Just something nice and
smooth to help it go down.
[MARTHA]
Our cider has some bite,
but I could certainly
water it down for you.
If you don't mind
paying a little more,
we have wine and mead.
Mead sounds perfect.
Done. I'll bring it
over to you right away.
Wow. This looks awesome!
[MARTHA] Wild boar steak
and vegetable soup!
And a mug of our
world-famous mead!
Best to eat it while it's hot!
[SATOU] I wasn't being polite,
this looks amazing.
I'll start with
the vegetable soup.
[SATOU] Mmm. The ingredients
are perfectly cooked.
The veggies melt in your mouth.
This is what I like
to call a mouth explosion!
The broth is tasty.
I bet this stuff sells
like crazy in the winter!
We're off to a great start.
Next up?
The main course:
wild boar steak.
The last boar I ate left
something to be desired.
Not to mention it
smelled like a shoe!
[SATOU]
It's great!
Not too lean,
but not too fatty either.
It's a little gamy,
but it's got this incredible
rustic flavor to it.
Way better than
your average slab of beef.
[SATOU] The bread's a little on
the tough side, but it's good.
You can tell this
loaf was made with love.
It's fun how crunchy it is!
Ahh...
It's perfection in a mug.
The hint of honey cuts against
the bitterness of the booze.
It's strong, too.
I better slow down!
You cleaned your plate.
You want some more?
Yes, I think I do.
[MARTHA giggles]
Right away.
[SATOU groans]
Round two was a mistake.
[SATOU]
But this inn is perfect.
The food's good
and the beds are clean.
The staff's cute, too.
It's the type of service
you could only find in a dream.
[SATOU]
I didn't see any dragons.
But that army of lizardmen
couldn't have been
more realistic.
That battle between
Zena and the wyvern
felt pretty damn real, too.
Like something out of a promo
video for a fantasy RPG!
Also, the level of detail
in Seiryuu City is insane!
The variation in the townspeople
alone is mind-blowing!
But hold on.
The things I've seen
in this world?
They don't really match up
with the games and stories
I know from my childhood.
[SATOU] I used to be a
huge nerd in middle school,
but I never dreamed up
something like this.
I'm experiencing
the taste of things
I've never even
imagined before.
[SATOU] This place is
way too vivid and weird
to be just a dream!
But if it isn't a dream.
Then what the hell is it?
It feels like a game,
but I can't log out
or save my progress.
What's the deal,
do I have to beat it to escape?
Do I have to win
to get out of here?
Wait.
In an MMO, the game never
really comes to an end.
[SATOU]
All right!
Whatever information
I need isn't in here!
Let's go!
Whatever this place is, I might
as well make the best of it.
I may not find a way home,
but as far as I'm concerned,
anything beats sitting
behind my stupid desk.
No more death marches
for yours truly.
[SATOU] Since it seems
like I'm stuck here,
I'm gonna do what the
younger me would do: have fun.
[MARTHA]
Hey, Satou!
Are you awake?
Morning, Martha.
[MARTHA] You need to hurry up
and get dressed right now.
Your girlfriend's waiting!
My girlfriend?
Good morning, Satou.
Sleep well?
Yeah, like a baby.
That's a lovely
outfit you have on.
What brings you
here this fine morning?
[ZENA]
Oh! Well...
I'm uh... I'm off-duty.
I was thinking I'd like to take
you on a quick tour of the city!