So, Satou,
do you have any plans
for this afternoon?
Yeah, actually,
I was gonna ask the
odd-jobs-people to help me
find housing that
accepts demi-humans.
The stables are fine.
But if I can find a
warm bed for them
to sleep in I'd
feel much better.
[ZENA]
Well...
Would it be all right
if I came with you?
[SATOU]
That would be awesome.
[SATOU] Are you sure that's how
you want to spend your day off?
Bumming around town with me?
Yes!
[SATOU]
Excuse me?
[NADI]
Coming!
So sorry for the delay.
Greetings, friends,
my name is Nadi.
My job here is to
make sure you find one!
Actually, I'm looking
for a property
to rent for my friends and me.
I can help with that, too.
Right this way, please, sir.
If you're sharing the
space with demi-humans,
it'll need to be in
the heart of West Town,
or at least somewhere
between there
and the worker's residences.
Good news and bad news.
Bad news is,
there's a lotta crime there.
But the good news is,
it's much cheaper.
So, what's your price range?
Well, with my budget.
Two silvers is the most
I'd prefer to spend.
But if that's not enough,
I'd be willing to go as
high as one gold coin.
At that price point,
your options are fairly limited.
That said, there are a couple
of places I can think of
off the top of my head that
should meet your requirements.
Shall we?
I should probably
tell you: A member
of the crime guild assassinated
the owner of this house.
Oh. Well, I guess that explains
why the price is so low.
[WORKER B]
You're showing that skin, honey,
and that's the name of the game.
[SATOU]
Yep.
That is a fully functioning
brothel right across the street.
Thanks but no thanks.
[SATOU]
The crime guild
has a hideout right
underneath this place,
complete with a secret tunnel
that leads into the city.
This one gives me a
bad feeling in my stomach.
I think it's a "no."
I understand.
[NADI]
Don't lose hope.
I'll head back to the office and
see if there are any properties
that are more
suitable to your needs.
[SATOU]
That'd be great, thanks.
I'll swing by
later this evening.
Hopefully you
have a little luck.
So what's next?
Is there anything you'd
like to do today, Zena?
Uh. No, what about you?
[NADI] Well, if you're
looking for something fun to do,
a new flea market just
opened in the plaza up ahead.
Generally speaking,
they have really modest prices
on most of their goods.
My manager and I were
actually planning to go, too.
[SATOU]
Interesting. Hmm...
[NADI] The outdoor theater
is absolutely to die for.
It's the perfect spot
for a date.
A date?
[SATOU]
Hmm? What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
[MALE VILLAGER A]
I'll take one!
[POCHI]
Lookie-loo!
It's the master!
Oh, yay!
How was the shopping, girls?
[POCHI]
Good!
[ARISA giggles]
The packages were heavy
so we dropped
them off at the inn.
But... look at my dress!
Master?
You like?
You look lovely!
Oh, your hair's different.
Yes, it is.
I was getting peculiar looks
on account of my purple hair.
I decided to make a change!
[SATOU]
Makes sense.
Master!
I'm glad you're here.
If it's all right, I have a
small favor to ask of you.
Don't cling to me.
If you need something, just ask.
[SATOU]
Cards, huh?
Art on the front.
The language of the
Saga Empire on the back.
Hey, this might come in handy
for teaching Pochi
and Tama how to read.
I like your cards.
That's kind of you to say, sir.
They're for learning Shigan!
[SATOU]
Wow!
The performance
is about to begin, Master.
If we don't hurry,
we might miss the show.
You lead the way, then.
[ARISA]
Did you buy tickets yet?
Tickets?
[LIZA]
Worry not, Master.
We'll take care of that part.
[SATOU]
Okay.
Here's some money.
I'm sorry about this, Zena.
But I promised Arisa I would
let the girls come to the play.
Oh. That's okay!
[SATOU]
Check it out.
I think these earrings
would compliment
your hair color nicely.
Wow.
They're so cute.
Do they suit me?
Yeah. For sure!
Thanks.
[ARISA]
Master! Master!
I want these so badly!
Well, In that case,
let's get something for Lulu,
and everybody else!
Hooray!
[SATOU] I wish Zena
would ask me for stuff.
It sure would make it
easier to shop for her.
Hi!
Wait until you see this!
[SATOU]
Excuse me.
Can I get these
earrings, please?
[HEIN]
Fair maiden!
Rather than under
the pale moonlight--
I would wish to see your
beautiful, smiling face
beneath the light
of the shining sun!
[IYUNA]
Oh! Beloved Zen!
Use a magic spell to
free me from this castle,
which to my weary
eyes seems an iron cell!
[SATOU] Tragic romances
are super freakin' lame.
Hungry!
I want some meat!
[SATOU]
I'm sorry about that.
It's fine.
[SATOU]
I guess they fell asleep.
What about Liza?
Whoa. She's into it!
No, wait.
Her tail's wagging,
which means she smells
those skewers cooking
right outside the theater.
[sighs]
[SATOU] This play,
"The Tragedy of Marquis Muno,"
is based on a true story.
The protagonist of the piece,
Zen, is a commoner wizard
who has a deep and
ultimately tragic romance
with Princess Liltiena.
Not only does her fiancé,
Marquis Muno, brutally murder
nearly every member
of Zen's extended family--
Zen himself is murdered by one
of the princess's attendants.
In the end, Princess Liltiena
takes her own life.
Which is what the audience
will want to do by
the end of the story.
[AUDIENCE shocked sounds]
It's just the audience.
[SATOU] Aww man,
I thought that was the end.
Wishful thinking, I guess.
[SATOU]
The body of the protagonist,
which was thrown from a cliff,
reanimates, becoming undead.
He goes on a violent rampage,
killing everyone at
the Marquis' estate.
Just as he's about to succeed?
Just as he's about
to kill the Marquis?
A Holy Knight kills him first.
Talk about anti-climactic.
Oh. Sweet Holy Knight!
[SATOU]
Not only that,
but the Marquis' whole
personality changes.
And then he dies because of
some weird, "bizarre-o"
curse from his marquisate.
The result is a finale
remarkable only for its opacity.
[SATOU]
Gabo flatbread?
Isn't gabo a vegetable
in that game Airrim ?
[SATOU]
You dropped this!
Thank you
for your kindness, sir.
Oh!
You're the young
man from the show!
[SATOU] Sorry again for
what happened back there.
It was nothing.
So what did you think about
the ending of the play?
Dreadful, wasn't it?
Uh. Well.
[FEMALE VILLAGER A] In the
script, the wizard is killed
by the Holy Knight after he gets
his revenge on the Marquis.
But the nobles complained,
so they changed the ending.
In the real story, the
princess is a commoner,
and yet, the marquis
desires her still.
Despite the fact that she's
married to another man,
the lecherous swine,
consumed with lustful
yearning, kidnaps her.
The nobles should have left well
enough alone if you ask me,
which of course nobody did!
[SATOU] So a bunch of idiots
meddled with a writer's work
and the result was
a complete disaster?
Shocking.
Ah!
[POCHI]
There you are, Master!
[TAMA]
We've been looking for you!
Sorry about that,
I had to use the bathroom.
[ARISA]
I loved it so much!
Wasn't that just the
most delightful story
you've ever heard?
It was beautiful.
I wept when the princess killed
herself after the wizard died.
So sad!
[ARISA]
Huh?
Instead of dying,
she should've secretly
taken that sword,
marched up to the marquis,
and stabbed him right
in his big ole stupid face!
The marquis was
the root of the problem,
trying to separate two
people who love each other!
Huh?
Perhaps. But it was the
princess who broke the promise
of the arranged marriage upon
which both families had agreed.
So in one sense,
the whole ordeal is her fault.
[ARISA]
Oh, come on!
Tell me: Who would you
rather marry, my master,
or some rich blowhard who
was forced down your throat?
Ah! Well...
I am not betrothed to anyone,
if you must know!
That's because you
joined the military,
so your parents couldn't force
you to marry against your will!
In these parts,
after women tie the knot,
they're in charge of
running the household,
but joining the military
means five years of service!
[SATOU] Is there something
going on here I don't get?
[ARISA]
...for the person you love,
then you have zero
business putting on a ring!
Forced marriage or not!
Yes. That's true.
But the head of the
family is still in charge!
[ARISA] Keep playing the good
girl and watch what happens.
You'll have your man stolen
right out from under you.
That was rude.
Ow!
Sorry about that, Zena.
Well, tell her you're sorry.
I'm sorry.
[SATOU]
Truth is,
I totally understand
what she means.
[SATOU]
So who wants meat skewers?
What? Are you for real?
Sounds like a plan to me!
Say the word
and it's done, Master.
How many skewers?
A lot, I guess?
Just make sure there's
enough for everyone.
I'll take care of the haggling!
Fun!
We're coming along, too!
[ZENA]
Lilio!
Zena!
You three look like
you were in a bad fight!
[IONA] A ferocious battle
with a herd of Fang Ants.
What?
The dirty rat
bastards got us good!
Next time I see 'em,
I'll eat those bugs for lunch!
[SATOU]
Fang Ants, huh?
Well, that sounds scary.
[IONA] The Fang Ants weren't
the only dubious characters
we came across.
We also spotted a large
unit of wererat cavalry
who crossed the border.
Ruu's theory?
The wererat riders were the ones
who attracted the
ants in the first place.
This much I know:
Their commander was
wearing a big red helmet.
If I ever find that villain,
he'll pay at the gallows!
Blow healing breeze!
[LILIO]
Thank you so much, Zena!
I'm glad you're safe.
Satou.
Sorry, but I have to go
help heal the other wounded.
[SATOU]
Of course!
[YUNI shrieks]
An ant!
A dead ant!
What are you doing
with that, you two?
[TAMA]
We killed it!
[POCHI]
It was attacking from above!
Be careful.
There might be more
monsters lurking nearby.
[SATOU]
Good job.
A "Flying Ant"?
I wonder if this is the same
type the border guards fought.
Red Markers!
Incoming!
Pochi, Tama.
Get your weapons!
--[POCHI] Okie-dokies!
--[TAMA] 'Kay!
[SATOU]
Arisa!
Go get Lulu!
On it!
[SATOU]
Liza.
Fetch the curtain we used for
the bed and get back here fast!
Understood, sir.
Is something wrong?
Don't worry, everything's
gonna be just--
[bell tolling]
Monster attack.
[SATOU] Flying Ants
are only level three.
They're not strong enough
to threaten armed guards.
But they've got sharp fangs
and hard exoskeletons.
Not to mention they can fly.
There're more than
enough of them
to do some substantial damage.
I could burn them all into
oblivion using Fire Shot,
but that'll draw way
too much attention.
[SATOU]
Those suckers are fast.
What the hell?
[ARISA] Looks like my protective
barrier above the city
is doing its part
to stave them off.
[SATOU] It's not doing its
job well enough, I'm afraid.
[ARISA] Do you know how much
MP I'd have to burn through
to create a magic barrier
as impenetrable
as a physical wall?
It's an unbelievable amount!
Arisa.
Take Lulu and go hide
in the back of that bar.
You got it.
[SATOU]
Pochi, Tama, protect the inn.
Okie-dokes.
Master, what will you do?
We need to focus our defense
on the main entry point.
It's time to build
a barricade, Liza!
[THORN]
Hurry up and get inside!
Don't lose heart, men,
it's one monster!
We've got nothing to fear!
Fallen Hammer!
[SOLDIER A]
Fire!
You ready?
Yes, Master.
I always am.
We won't let you through, ants!
Sorry! Road's closed!
Hyah! All right!
Ah!
That was a close one!
Thank you so much, Tama!
Fuhgeddaboudit.
[SATOU] She sounded just
like a movie mobster.
Did Arisa teach her that?
[SATOU]
She must've used psychic magic.
Looks like a few
of the ants made it
inside the building
where Nadi works.
It's settling outside.
Liza!
I'll let you take it from here!
All right!
[SATOU]
Nadi! Are you okay?
[NADI]
Yes! I think so!
[SATOU] The stairs are
covered in ant poison.
Guess I could smash a rock
and use it for footing.
[YUSARATOYA spell chant]
Ivy Control!
Manager?
You saved me, Satou.
Thank you.
[NADI]
And one for you, too.
Thank you.
[NADI]
You're so welcome.
I am very grateful, sir.
[YUSARATOYA]
Who's this?
He came here looking for
a place to rent earlier.
And then he saved
me from the ants.
Thank you.
[SATOU] The fantasy world's
most popular race by far.
An elf!
[NADI]
Is something the matter?
Oh, no.
It's just I don't think
I've ever met someone
with green hair.
[NADI]
Heh. Well, his hair is green
because he is an
elvish forest spirit.
[SATOU] Wait a second,
I thought elves had long ears.
[YUSARATOYA]
Hmph. How rude.
Oh, no, that's a different
race called the Long-ears.
And don't worry,
it happens a lot.
And, in fact, it always has.
Since the first hero called
the Long-ears, "elves."
It's hard to believe,
but people have been making
that mistake for well over
a millennium now.
Truth is,
elves hate being
mistaken for a Long-ear.
Isn't that right, Manager, sir?
I honestly didn't know.
Manager, please
forgive me for my ignorance.
[YUSARATOYA]
You're forgiven.
Ya see?
Oh my.
[SATOU] We can discuss the
housing situation another time.
[NADI]
Right!
Thank you again for saving me!
[SATOU]
Crisis averted.
Ah! Oh, there you are!
Ah!
Are you all right?
Yes.
So sorry.
[ZENA] We're all lucky to
have survived that ordeal.
Well, I'd better join my
fellow guardsmen in town.
They'll need me if any bugs
slipped through our ranks.
[SATOU]
What a shame.
It's your day off, and
here you are, working again.
I'm really disappointed
that our day together
ended the way it did.
But even so,
it was a lot of fun spending
some time with you.
I should go.
I'm sure there are more coming.
I need to be there to help
fend them off when they do.
[SATOU]
Be careful!
Bye!
[SOLDIER B] Does this
slave belong to you, kid?
I am back, Master.
The law says that
all persons are required
to sell their cores to
the city government, sir.
[SATOU]
One moment.
[SOLDIER B]
Hmm?
We just need to
draw up a receipt first.
Give it a look, sir.
This'll show the number
of cores and the amount paid.
Oh yeah.
It'll show your name
and identification, as well.
Now, look here, kid.
I hope you're not insinuating
I was gonna steal them!
[SATOU]
Not at all.
But you can never
be too careful.
You're a good man.
But it doesn't matter
if you're a holy saint.
If you wanna purchase my cores?
Then I'm gonna need
a receipt, mister.
[SOLDIER B groans]
Good enough for you?
Your numbers are wrong, friend.
And there's no seal.
Let's fix that.
[SOLDIER B]
I just forgot is all!
[SATOU] These days,
everybody's out to make a buck.
[ARISA]
What a lovely meal!
Ya know what
that smell is, girls?
Joy!
Time to eat meat!
Just a little longer, ladies.
These two girls are
something else, Satou.
They're tiny as little teacups,
yet they still protected
my inn from harm.
Nyan.
[MOSA] I can never
repay you for your bravery.
But I'll tell you what I'll do:
Let me get my husband to whip up
his best meal and make you
a feast you'll never forget!
[GIRLS]
Bless this food!
[SATOU] I guess Lulu's
not feeling any better.
[SATOU] Maybe there's
a pharmacy in town.
[MALE VILLAGER C]
Oh, Young Master!
[MALE VILLAGER D] Aren't you
the kid from the labyrinth
the other day?
Yeah.
[MALE VILLAGER C]
We're not gonna let our savior
walk the streets
at night all alone.
Come on, let us buy you a drink.
[SATOU] Uh. Actually,
I was heading somewhere.
Hey, don't worry, buddy,
it's just one drink.
Bye bye!
Come and see us
anytime you want!
[SATOU]
That escalated quickly.
I thought they were
gonna buy me a beer,
not take me to a brothel.
[SATOU]
The feather of a Shadow Owl?
Maybe Pochi and
Tama would like this.
[SATOU]
Monsters?
[gasps]
[SATOU]
Are you all right?
[MIZE]
Who are you?
[SATOU]
A red helmet.
[MIZE]
Who are you?
Tell me the truth:
Are you one of his men?
Whose men?
Huh? What's this?
I won't make it much
longer, I'm afraid.
Please.
Take care of the princess.
[SATOU]
Hang in there!
[SATOU] Nadi's status
says she's asleep.
The manager's too.
I've no choice.
[NADI]
Uh, Manager?
Are you going to join me in bed?
[YUSARATOYA]
No.
[SATOU] I feel bad for how
into that Nadi just sounded.
[SATOU]
Good evening.
Sorry to intrude.
It's Satou.
Is something wrong?
[SATOU] I brought someone
who knows the manager.
He's hurt.
I was hoping you would
be able to help heal him
with a magic spell.
[YUSARATOYA spell chant]
Mana Light.
I recognize that red helmet.
I might be mistaken,
but from what I've heard,
he could be Red Mask,
the infamous wererat knight.
Have we met?
[SATOU]
No.
He's not the one
I'm referring to.
[gasps]
[NADI]
I think that's an elf!
[YUSARATOYA]
Mia.