[SATOU]
Perfect.
I should make the 8:33 train
without any problems.
[SATOU]
Oh, crap!
It's running early!
[pants]
Adulting is hard.
Life was a whole lot easier
back when I was school.
Oh, yeah.
Forgot it was Sunday.
That's why the train schedule
is running differently.
I can't believe I forgot
what day it was.
[SATOU]
Good morning.
Hey.
Are you seriously working
over the weekend again?
[SATOU]
Always.
We're slammed right now.
You know, cause of the new guy.
Uh, yeah. That's right.
I can't believe he
just up and quit,
especially right before
the delivery date?
So you're picking up the slack?
[SATOU]
Who else?
But with all the bugs and
changes in the core design,
we might not make deadline.
[COWORKER A] You're a
good guy, you know that?
I hope the brass brings
in some new people, ASAP.
[SATOU] Turnover didn't
used to be this brutal.
But now?
Seems like someone
quits everyday.
[COWORKER A]
You're a real grown up, man.
I'm staring down 30.
Better late than never.
Welp.
It's time to start
another death march.
[SATOU]
Okay.
Finish line approaching.
I'm done writing all the classes
and commenting everything.
Now I just gotta generate the
documentation and UML
from the source code, and start
drilling down on the bugs.
The end is so close
I can taste it.
Not again, man.
You can't keep changing stuff
I've already
gone over like this.
[SATOU]
Hmph.
[TUBBY]
Sato-- I mean, Suzuki.
You and I need to
talk War World , bro.
[SATOU] He just tried
to call me Satou again.
We've been working
together for six months.
He should know my name by now.
[TUBBY] We gotta
major problem on our hands:
the client is saying the game's
too difficult for beginners.
If we don't fix it
before the delivery date,
we are totally screwed.
Huh? I know the
client is always right,
but they told us our target
audience won't play the game
if we make it any easier.
Uh, I guess you're right.
There's another way.
We should use my idea,
the one that got axed early on.
When you create your avatar, you
get an item that reveals a map
and three heavy-duty bombs.
Cool.
[SATOU] If you clear the area
without using the short cut,
you get a rare achievement.
Two birds, one stone.
Beginners are taken care of,
and skilled gamers have
something to play for.
[TUBBY]
Since we're under the gun,
how about we just go with that?
Good thinking, Suzuki,
I'll leave the rest to you!
Hold on a sec!
Yes?
I still have to fix all the bugs
in that mobile MMORPG,
so I'm running
kinda short on time.
While I'm busy with that,
call the client and
get them to sign off.
If I put in that feature
and the client says "no,"
we won't make deadline.
Yeah. Right.
I'm calling
to confirm right now.
[SATOU]
I guess I'll go get some lunch.
[SATOU] There's always an
event out here, even on Sunday.
[GIRL cries]
[SATOU]
Is she lost?
[sighs]
[SATOU]
Hey. You're all right.
What's wrong? Are you lost?
[GIRL cries]
My mama.
[SATOU] I have no
idea what's she's saying.
I guess I should probably
take her to a police station.
Right.
Come on, let's go get help.
[MOTHER]
Mana!
[GIRL]
Mommy!
Oh. There you are, my love!
[SATOU]
Oh. Is she your daughter?
She is.
I'm very sorry if
she bothered you, sir.
[SATOU] Please.
She was no trouble at all.
I'm just glad you found her.
That's a load off.
For a second I was
worried she might think
I was some kind of creep.
Thank you for taking
care of my sweet girl.
[SATOU]
Sure!
[GIRL] I want chocolate
ice cream in a cone
with sprinkles on top!
[SATOU]
Her mom is pretty hot, though.
All right.
That should do it.
I guess I should test it out.
[SATOU]
Wait.
What was the name
of the game again?
Oh, yeah!
FFL .
[COWORKER B]
Good work.
[SATOU]
Huh?
Headed out?
Haven't been home in three days.
Gotta get back there fast
before the wife kicks me out.
Hey, at least you have someone
at home who actually cares.
[COWORKER B]
That's true.
Playing the field's fun, but you
don't want to do it forever.
Am I right?
You're 29 years old, dude.
You need to find
yourself a lady, my friend.
See ya.
[SATOU]
Huh... A lady.
Would be nice.
But when every day
is a death march?
That's a pretty
unrealistic proposition.
Man, I sure could use a bath.
[SATOU]
I'm almost finished.
One last email
and then I'm home free.
Suzuki!
We just got a bug report
from the storage testing team.
What?
No, that can't be right,
I literally just spent
the last couple of hours
fixing the storage space bug.
[COWORKER C] I'm not
talking about the inventory
in FFL , dude.
I'm talking about a new one:
There's an item duplication
bug in World War .
Check your messenger.
I just sent you an
attachment with the details.
[SATOU]
All right.
Duplication bugs
are hard to fix.
I see.
The jerk didn't
want to get yelled at,
so he sent me an email.
He better take me out
to lunch somewhere nice
with tons of cute girls!
[SATOU sighs]
Done at last!
Huh?
[SATOU] I'm sure there are some
bugs left, but it'll be fine.
Digital distribution lets us
patch it later down the line.
I can hear the
users complaining now.
But I don't care.
If I can just
fire off this email,
I can finally get some sleep.
[SATOU]
I really needed this.
I haven't shut my eyes
in over 30 hours.
Right now.
Sleep is my justice.
What the heck is this?
Am I dreaming?
Huh?
[SATOU] Of course
the phone doesn't work.
Whoa! I'm young!
Whoa! I look like
I did back in high school.
[sighs]
Well, having a dream
about your younger self
isn't that abnormal.
[SATOU]
But then again.
This is a little freaky.
Don't get me wrong.
When I'm on a death march,
I have dreams about
fixing bugs all the time.
But I don't think I've ever had
a dream where my younger self
is actually inside the freakin'
game I'm working on.
It's crazy.
It's kind of like War World
and FFL got slammed together.
And of course it has bugs.
[SATOU]
Whoa.
I just did that with my mind.
Satou.
That's the name I always
use for my test characters
when I'm working out bugs.
[SATOU]
The Valley of Dragons?
Well, I guess that's what
this massive crevice is.
[SATOU]
Uh! What's that?
Uh-oh.
Crap.
Weapons?
Looks like all I've got
are three Meteor Rains
and a Map Reveal.
Wait.
This is the idea I came up with
to help out beginning players.
The map!
[SATOU] Red dots only
mean one thing: bad guys!
[SATOU]
Elite lizardmen?
That doesn't sound fun!
There are hundreds of them
and they're all level 50!
I'm only level one!
I can't beat them in
a hand-to-hand fight!
[SATOU]
I really hate lizardmen.
Oh crap! Please tell me
they don't know I'm here!
[SATOU] I felt that.
I for real just felt that!
[SATOU]
This sucks.
I'm gonna have to fight back!
No way!
My weaponry hasn't
implemented yet!
Aww man!
I'm about to die here.
And all because of a damn bug!
[SATOU]
Satou here.
I've been a busy
little worker bee,
like any good citizen of a
thriving democracy should be.
Work's been tough lately,
I won't lie, but not so tough
I want to disappear
to another dimension.
I was busy.
But it made me feel important.
That's the truth.
[SATOU coughs]
Oh no. Crap.
[SATOU] That lizard was too
close to be in the target range
of the meteor strike.
Stick a fork in me.
Rahr-reh-kuhn.
Freh-streen.
Condeen-stuhn gah-dreen.
[SATOU]
This is exactly like a game.
He wants me to fight him.
With this sword.
[screams]
Ow! That hurt! Like, a lot!
[SATOU] Looks like his
life bar is almost gone.
Gotta keep fighting!
[SATOU] I've heard of
people having vivid dreams,
but this is too much!
There has to be a way to get
out of this freakin' nightmare!
Like an off button.
[SATOU]
What?
I can't save
my progress or log out?
You're not very nice
to your players, dream!
[sighs]
This sucks.
I need to figure out a way to
heal, at least until I wake up.
Am I already healed?
Oh, wow.
And it feels like the
pain's all gone, too.
Wait a sec.
My max vitality has increased!
And that's not all.
I'm level 310?
This rules.
I must've leveled up
due to the Meteor Rain.
I guess that explains
why I was able
to take out that lizard
freak one-on-one.
[SATOU] Whoa, my ability
points are maxed out, too.
Wait a second, where's the log?
Keep scrolling, keep scrolling.
I'll skip anything that
doesn't make sense.
If this is a log of everything.
What about skills?
I've gotten more magic skill.
I have that
Meteor Rain I just used.
But I wonder if that
means it's disabled?
I guess I just have
to turn it back on.
Typical gaming platform.
Even in a dream,
these things are complicated.
Whatever.
I better test it out while
I still have the chance.
If I get into another sticky
situation with those lizardmen
and it tells me I don't have
enough MP, I'm gonna be pissed!
Not to mention dead.
This should be a
safe enough distance.
Huh?
[SATOU]
Uh-oh. Not good.
[screams]
[SATOU]
That magic is way too powerful.
If I use it all the time,
I might as well declare
myself a super villain.
I think I'd better play it safe.
Bye, bye.
[sighs]
I'm really thirsty.
[SATOU]
There's loot, too.
[SATOU] Huh? Lizardman
corpses count as loot?
[SATOU]
Cool. I have a water pouch.
Let's see
if I can use it though.
Nice!
It appeared!
[SATOU]
Oh, wow!
This is the best water
I've tasted in my entire life!
Unlimited fresh water.
No idea how that's possible,
but it's pretty sweet.
I wonder what else I have.
[SATOU]
I'm loaded up with cash!
I don't feel like organizing
this right now.
But the next time
I come across a town,
I'm gonna have a field day!
[SATOU] A holy sword,
a divine sword, and a magic gun?
Man, I feel like I died and went
to middle school geek heaven!
Ohh!
Wow.
Nice.
[SATOU]
It's weird.
I don't have many skills.
I wonder if you get more
via some sort of action
instead of by leveling up.
I guess I'll add points
to things I'll need in battle.
If I come across an army of
lizardmen, I wanna be prepared.
[SATOU] Well, I should
probably get some sleep
before I head out.
Besides, exploring
is my favorite part.
[SATOU]
All right.
I guess I'll head to this
"Warrior's Fort" place first.
This place rocks.
I've been slaving away in front
of a computer for so long.
I forgot what beauty looks like.
I know this dream
isn't gonna last forever.
But it's a nice escape
while it does.
All right.
Here goes!
[SATOU]
So this is Warrior's Fort?
Oh. A monarchy. "Seiryuu City."
That's the closest
place to the fort.
There are about 100 soldiers.
Highest-level soldier
here is only 31.
Average level is 7.
That's pretty low.
What's that?
A wyvern, eh?
Let's check it out!
[shrieks]
That hurt.
No, it didn't.
Do I have a pain
reduction skill?
Or maybe it's 'cause my
endurance is really high?
Suck on this, wyvern!
I'm super strong.
Level 310 is no joke.
Huh?
[SATOU]
Wait a sec.
That wyvern's heading
towards the soldiers!
This is my fault.
I have to help them.
[incomprehensible yelling]
[gasps]
[SATOU] Huh? I need to
change the language settings.
[MALE SOLDIER A]
Soldiers! Hold your ground!
[MALE SOLDIER B]
Show them our Seiryuu courage!
Here it comes!
Hold strong to your
positions and don't relent!
Dig in your heels, lancemen!
Let your feet in the air, and
the wyvern will blow you away!
[FEMALE SOLDIER A]
Bowmen! Draw it in!
Wait for the lances to slow
its speed, and then we strike!
[SATOU]
Those arrows aren't sharp enough
to penetrate the wyvern's hide.
Then again it might
not be the arrows,
it could be the
soldiers' levels are too low.
Tumultuosum!
[MAGE A]
Four winds, Aero hammer!
Lightning Bolt Shock Attack!
[SATOU]
It's coming!
Zena, stop him!
Right!
Four winds I summon thy power!
Aero Forcefield!
[MAGE B]
Resist Fall Gravity Barrier!