Oh! My goodness, it's an elf!
Mia.
Pretty.
[MIZE coughs]
We need to get him some help,
or he's not going to make it!
Stay with him.
I'll be back as quickly
as I possibly can!
It's too dangerous
to go out at night alone.
Let me go with you!
[ARISA]
Awww!
You snuck off to a brothel
in the middle of the night?
Nasty!
Why would you pay for services I
would gladly give you for free?
I am deeply offended, Master!
Not cool.
[ARISA]
I smell boy!
[SATOU]
She's insane.
Ahh... It smells like dog.
Tell the truth.
Where else did you go?
Hmph!
Last night,
when I went to
get medicine for Lulu.
I saved the life of
a wererat knight.
[groans]
Was it a girl knight?
Actually, no.
If you really wanna know,
it was an old man.
Oh dear!
It's boy love?
You were doing god-knows-what in
the forest with a filthy animal!
Probably rolling in the mud
with a big hunk
of man-beast flesh!
Ooo!
That sounds fun!
[SATOU] Could you
stop spouting nonsense?
Get dressed.
That's an order.
Huh?
[SATOU]
Oh. How are you?
Good.
I feel better than
yesterday, that's for sure.
I bought you some meds.
You'll be feeling
better in no time.
Oh. You're very kind, Master.
[SATOU] After everyone
finishes breakfast,
I should probably head
to the General Store.
Morning, Nadi.
How are they doing?
Well.
At the moment,
they're still sleeping.
Mia doesn't appear to be
injured, but she needs her rest.
The poor thing was on
the verge of exhaustion.
According to the manager,
Mia is exhibiting
classic symptoms
of prolonged MP deprivation.
[SATOU]
Hmm...
[NADI] The manager tried
multiple forms of magic on her.
He tried Mana Transfer,
a practical magic.
And he tried Stamina Charge,
a Forest Magic.
But nothing worked.
[SATOU]
Judging from her titles,
I'd say she's probably
about 11 years old.
She's not cursed or sick.
And it seems like her MP is
recovering, slowly but surely.
There's only one way to
speed up the process, Satou.
A mana potion.
But those tonics aren't cheap.
We could take her to
a place rich with mana,
like a ley line intersection
or a good mana source.
Huh? Mana source?
Yes. But around these parts,
our options are a bit scarce.
There's only the Count's castle
and the Valley of the Dragons.
[gasps]
I just heard some
movement upstairs.
I think your guests are awake.
[NADI]
Mia. Are you feeling okay?
Yes.
[NADI]
My name is Nadi and I work here.
Another elf, Yusaratoya,
owns this place, though.
Yuya?
Man.
There.
[NADI]
Oh! That's Satou!
He saved your life, Mia, you and
your friend with the red helmet.
Satou?
[NADI]
Is it all right if he comes in?
Yes.
[SATOU]
Hi, there.
I'm Satou, a merchant.
It's nice to meet you.
[MIA]
A Spirit User?
No.
I don't think I've ever
used a spirit before.
[MIA]
Can't see them?
Are those something
people can see?
[NADI]
Yes.
But spirits are
only visible to people
who have the
gift of Spirit Sight.
[SATOU]
That's awesome.
I guess Spirit Sight
is rare, even for an elf.
Are you hungry, Mia?
[MIA]
Yes.
[NADI] I'll go whip up
something in the kitchen,
maybe some hot wheat porridge.
Satou, would you mind looking
after her while I'm gone?
[SATOU]
Not at all.
So about these spirits,
what are they like?
Fluffy.
[SATOU]
Uh... Fluffy?
Yes. Sparkly.
[SATOU]
Eh, sparkly?
She's not exactly a talker.
I need to figure out a way to
get her to open up a little bit.
Wait! I know!
So,
Mia, how do you say,
"Good morning," in elvish?
Teparusa.
[SATOU]
It was like pulling teeth,
but I did manage to
pry some info out of her.
Apparently, spirits flow
along the ley lines
subsisting on mana.
Sorry for sticking
around so long.
I should probably get going.
Stay.
[ARISA]
All right!
Victory is mine!
Ahhh!
Aww, man!
Arisa wins every time!
Pochi, Tama, if the two
of you have time to sulk,
then you most certainly
have time to get better!
Arisa's really smart!
Hey, wait.
The cards from yesterday.
Look, you guys: it's Master!
Having fun, girls?
[TAMA]
We learned some words!
Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah. Cool!
So cool!
Quiz time.
What's this card say?
[POCHI]
That one says, "Meat"!
[SATOU]
Nope.
Goat.
And this one?
Also meat!
[SATOU]
Sorry. Rabbit.
Hmm...
Yes, well.
Technically, they're
not wrong, Master.
All animals are meat in a
certain sense of the word.
I suppose you're
right about that.
But the answer is not meat.
To get it right, you have
to name the actual animal.
I understand!
This meat is a goat, right?
Yeah.
And this meat is a
bouncy bunny rabbit!
Then my card does
not mean poultry,
but rather the
very chicken itself!
[SATOU]
Huh?
[POCHI] How do you
write "meat," Master?
[SATOU]
Like this.
[MARTHA] Yuni! I've been
looking everywhere for you!
I'm sorry about that, Martha.
You still behave like a
little kid, do you know that?
Come. We need to get to work.
We have to clean up the stables
and replace the hay
before it's time for lunch!
But, Martha,
I already did all that.
Huh?
Pochi and Tama helped me
finish my chores this morning.
That's right!
We were some cleaning fools!
I picked up the horse poo!
Wow, girls.
I'm impressed.
Yeah, we know!
[LIZA] A princess, under
the protection of a wererat?
Oh, Master!
I wanna meet her!
[TAMA] I've never heard of
a wererat princess before.
[POCHI]
Yeah, me neither!
How fun!
Well.
After we finish eating lunch,
let's all go say, "Hello," then.
Sounds like fun.
I'm in!
All righty!
Okie-dokey-smokey!
I'm so excited to meet her!
[TAMA] Aww, I wish
we could go right now!
[SATOU]
How about it, Lulu?
You feeling up to it?
We'd love for you to come.
'Kay.
[ARISA]
I'll go first!
Hello, my name is Arisa!
My name is Pochi!
I'm Tama.
Mia.
Oh!
Wow, she's a pretty princess!
I love her hair so much!
[ARISA]
Master!
I don't understand;
you said she was a rat girl!
No, I didn't.
I said she was a princess
who was being guarded
by a wererat knight.
--[TAMA] Mia!
--[ARISA] Mia!
[POCHI]
It's nice to meet you!
[ARISA]
Look at your hair!
So plush!
[TAMA]
Can I touch it?
I'm gonna head downstairs.
Look after Mia, for me, 'kay?
Okay!
Okie-doke, Master!
We really like Mia!
Stay.
[SATOU] Jeez. I wonder
what's got her so attached.
[NADI]
What a relief.
All I had for breakfast today
was some wheat porridge.
Thanks a lot.
Remind me, Satou.
You're a merchant, aren't you?
Uh. Yeah.
I mean, I guess.
I haven't exactly
been selling my wares.
Why don't you have a cart, then?
[SATOU]
Well.
I had a horse carrying my stuff.
But sadly, when the starfall hit
it got spooked and ran away.
[NADI]
I'm sorry to hear that.
You know.
If you can afford it, you
should probably purchase one.
I would buy a drawn cart.
[SATOU]
A drawn cart?
The manager is friendly
with an older merchant
who is planning to
retire from business soon.
If you have any interest,
he's going to be selling two
horses and a cart as well.
[SATOU]
Hmm...
I really appreciate
the offer, Nadi.
But I don't know how
to drive one of those.
Uh. I um...
[SATOU]
Lulu.
There's no need to be shy, okay?
[LULU]
Yes.
Master,
I just wanted to tell you
that I have some experience
driving a one-horse cart.
[SATOU]
Awesome.
Maybe you can teach me then.
Huh?
[SATOU]
Nadi.
Tell the manager's contact
I'm very interested.
That was a snap decision.
Don't you want to know
about the price, Satou?
[SATOU]
Oh, yeah, the price.
Not bad.
I think I'll buy one after all.
Here take this.
Let's just say this is as
much as I'm willing to pay.
Whatever's left over, you can
keep as a "thank you" tip.
Oh my.
[SATOU] That was probably a
little too generous on my part.
I'm a terrible merchant.
This is a perfect spot
for camping lessons,
don't you think, girls?
--[TAMA] Yeah!
--[POCHI] Okie-dokeies!
[TAMA]
You want us to weed?
[POCHI]
Don't worry! We got this!
Look how strong I am!
[TAMA]
This is really heavy.
Check it out, girls!
We're all stocked up!
Try a kettle!
[POCHI]
It's weird, right?
[TAMA]
Yeah.
The kettle's really mad at us!
He's about to blow his top!
The kettle man is super scary!
[SATOU]
The kettle man?
Relax.
It's nothing.
Just a whistle to let you
know the water is boiling.
He seems pretty mad.
How come he doesn't just say,
"Hey, I'm about to boil"?
[SATOU]
It's not a "he." It's an "it."
The water gets so hot
in there it turns to vapor.
[ARISA] What are you, some
kind of science teacher nerd?
They're just kids.
You can't possibly
expect them to understand
that water gets one thousand
times bigger when it boils.
[SATOU] Don't you mean sixteen
hundred times bigger, Arisa?
[ARISA]
Look girls.
Water turns into a
white smoke called steam,
but only when it
gets really hot.
The hotter it gets,
the stronger the steam.
That's what causes
the lid to move like that.
Look.
Just like you create force
when you blow out air,
the water creates force when
it turns to steam and rises up!
She's so awesome!
You're a genius, Arisa!
[POCHI]
Tama! Do the rolly-roll!
[TAMA]
It's rolly-roll-time!
Tama! Way to go!
[POCHI] You're quite
the rolly-roller, Tama!
[TAMA]
Your turn, Pochi!
[SATOU]
Aren't they...?
[DEMI-HUMAN A] This is for
the grill chicken you gave us.
You were kind. Thank you.
It was very yummy, too.
[SATOU]
What's this?
Present for you! Fresh fruit!
[TAMA]
What are you guys doing?
[POCHI] You guys get away
from our master right now!
Calm down.
They just gave me some
fruit as a thank-you gift
for a kindness I paid them.
Yeah.
Huh?
This is Cee nut, Master!
It's really yummy!
Is this Kuko berry?
It's my favorite treat!
Give back! It is for him!
[SATOU]
I have to take it.
They went to all this trouble.
But something tells me they need
the fruit way more than I do.
I know!
I'll gladly accept this gift.
But I do have one small request.
See this jerky?
We have so much
we can't eat it all.
Would you take some please?
--Meat!
So kind. You sure?
[SATOU]
Yes.
You'd be helping me out.
[DEMI-HUMANS]
Thank you! Thank you!
[NADI] You are now officially
the owner of this cart, Satou.
[SATOU]
Thank you, Nadi.
We can definitely carry
a lot more stuff this way.
[ARISA]
Say.
Why don't we use
our brand new cart
to take sweet Mia back home?
Hold on. Home?
Where is home to Mia, anyway?
[NADI]
The elf village.
It's just southeast
of the Shiga Kingdom.
I see.
Well,
we should talk it over with the
manager when he gets back.
Before we do
anything else though,
I need to learn how
to drive this cart.
I'm counting on you, Lulu.
Pretty weather today.
Oh, yes.
It's pretty indeed.
You know there's no need
to be nervous, right?
I know that you're shy.
But it's cool.
You can relax around me,
like Pochi and Tama do.
Oh no. I am a slave, Master.
It's important that
I keep my place.
[SATOU]
I tried.
But she's about as
forthcoming as the elf princess.
I think I know a topic that'll
make her come out of her shell.
Arisa's great!
She's the best
sister of all time!
[SATOU]
People always talk eventually,
they just need
the right subject.
You really love your
sister a lot, don't you?
Yes!
I bet if you didn't know you'd
think I was the younger sibling.
[SATOU]
Yeah.
Can't believe she's just 11.
She's been a prodigy ever
since we were both little girls.
[SATOU]
I wonder if Arisa told Lulu
she has memories
from her past life.
[LULU] No one had to
teach her that stuff either,
she just knew things!
[SATOU] How about we move
on to the cart lesson, Lulu.
[LULU]
Uh, sorry.
When I talk about my sister,
I blab.
[SATOU]
Must be hard for her.
Huh?
Um, Sir?
Is something the matter?
I'm fine.
It's just I saw a big bird in
the trees and got distracted.
Sorry.
Master, you came back to us!
[POCHI]
We missed you!
So much!
We're very glad you didn't die.
Hello.
Mia, you're up?
You sure you
should be outta bed?
[MIA]
Yes. Used potions.
The manager brought
Mia some magic potions,
and they helped her a lot.
I don't know
what kind they were,
but they got the job done right!
[SATOU]
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Oh. Thank you.
[SATOU]
Your hair looks cool.
It suits you.
Cool.
Ooo! Since she's on
the road to recovery,
let's eat something delicious
for dinner to celebrate!
[SATOU]
Great idea.
What sounds good, Mia?
Honey buns.
Uh, honey buns?
Ever since
Pochi and Tama told her
how delectable honey buns are,
the poor thing can't
stop talking about them!
Honey buns are so good!
I'd eat them every
single day of my life!
Seems to me
the right thing to do
is to get these dears
some honey buns!
Don't you mean you
want some for yourself?
Well.
Liza, Lulu?
Let's do this thing.
[LULU]
Right!
[LIZA]
We're on it.
Bye. Bye!
See you later!
[TAMA]
Be safe!
[gasps]
[POCHI]
What's the matter?
Uh... That's a weird bird.
[SATOU]
It's the one I saw before.
[laughs]
[POCHI]
Guess who's back?
Satou.
I was hoping you would drop by.
The manager and Mize
are having a little talk.
Mize?
[knock, knock]
Satou.
Satou?
My good, sir.
Are you the human
who saved my life?
[SATOU]
Mize, the wererat knight.
Now.
I can finally get the answers
I've been waiting for.
Mia was kidnapped
from her quiet elf village
by a band of wizards.
She was imprisoned in
a place called the Cradle.
Luckily, she was able to escape.
On the run,
she bumped into Mize.
They made for Seiryuu City,
hoping to meet up
with the manager.
The wizards who
kidnapped Mia were furious,
so they sent the Flying Ants
to attack the city.
We don't know why Mia
was kidnapped exactly.
But...
...the manager seems
to have an idea.
[SATOU]
Huh?
However, since he doesn't
appear inclined to share,
I'll leave well enough alone.
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
I need to talk to him about
escorting Mia back home.
[thunder clap]
[GIRLS scream]
[YUSARATOYA]
Nadi!
Oh, Manager!
[SATOU]
No bad guys around.
[GIRLS scream]
[SATOU]
I see.
They're scared of thunder.
Why is the
lighting man so scary?
A flash then a boom!
Then a terrifying darkness!
It splits trees in two!
[MIA]
Lightning is dangerous.
I know this!
Aze told me.
Even big dragons get
knocked out of the sky
by a lightning strike!
They shake the ground
when they land!
[SATOU]
Aze?
Are you scared
of lightning, too?
Duh! Who isn't?
Huh?
[SATOU]
Tama.
What's wrong?