[MIZE]
He's here!
[SATOU]
Psychic Magic?
His power!
It's overwhelming!
[gasps]
Arisa's fighting back.
[SATOU]
There! The Resistance Skill!
Zen?
Where've I heard
that name before?
[SATOU]
The hero from that play!
[ZEN]
I have come to retrieve you.
Mia.
Mr. Sorcerer Man,
glad to meet you.
My name's Satou.
I'm a merchant.
[ZEN] Huh? I have no need
for a simple merchant.
I'll admit, I'm amazed you can
hold your ground, unshaken,
while withstanding my power.
It's impressive, even
for a Hero's descendant.
[SATOU]
Wait.
A Hero's descendant?
[ZEN] My intention was
to let you live, but defy me,
and I will show no mercy.
I'm not really
the violent type, sir.
But Mia's my friend.
If you think I'll let
you steal her away,
you're a bigger fool
than you look.
I think it's time
for you to leave.
[ZEN]
You're the fool.
If you want to protect Mia,
you'll do so by force.
I am not interested
in making peace.
Only in achieving
my purpose here.
Well, have it your way then.
Ahh!
This guy can control shadows.
[ZEN]
Impressive.
Are you a merchant?
Or a martial artist?
Either way, for someone at your
level, it's quite impressive.
I'm impressed, too.
I never met a sorcerer
who can move shadows.
So we're even.
[ZEN] In spite of your doom,
you run your mouth still.
What a courageous spirit.
Get your damn hands off
my master, you creep!
A wraith!
[ZEN]
How dare you insult me, slave?
I am no wraith.
No low-level undead minion!
[SATOU]
This oughta do the trick!
[gasps]
[ZEN]
No!
No! It's simply not possible!
Nothing in this world
should be able to interact
with the power of my Shadow
Whip except a magic item!
We can beat this guy!
No. Just run.
[ARISA] You really think I'd
leave you behind and run away?
I'm not trying to protect you
because we're friends.
I'm doing it because my master
wants to keep you safe.
What my master wants,
my master gets!
Always!
Yes, but--
There're no buts about it!
We're saving you, Mia,
no matter what you say!
[SATOU]
Is she about to use magic?
Hold on.
Sorcerer.
You already know who we are.
It's only fair for you
to tell us, too.
Although, it's pretty
obvious already.
The highest rank of the undead.
An Undead King.
[ZEN] Hmm...
You say you're a merchant,
yet you fight like
a martial artist.
And now you wield that
like a veteran gunman.
Oh, I've got plenty
of tricks up my sleeve.
[ZEN]
Yes, indeed you do, Satou.
Shall we add "hero"
to your many identities?
Master, quickly!
Jump out of the way!
[ZEN gasps]
[pants]
[ZEN]
That was certainly a close one.
To think she'd
have a unique skill.
[ZEN]
And that hair color.
It seems you're
reincarnated as well.
I tried, Master.
[SATOU]
It's not working at all.
[ZEN] Strength beyond one's
capacity brings only ruin.
If you would keep
her from becoming
a plaything for the gods,
then you should keep her
from using that unique skill.
Thanks for the advice, pal.
[ZEN]
You're quite welcome.
I shall take my leave now.
Huh?
[ZEN]
It's useless.
To defeat one who
has transcended nature,
you must possess the means to
defy the laws of nature itself!
No! Satou!
[SATOU]
Mia!
[ZEN] If you truly have no fear
of death, then visit the Cradle.
It would give me immense
pleasure to see you
push your wisdom and
courage to their limits,
in an attempt to strike me down.
Master!
Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay!
The others need your help now!
Go get Zena as
quickly as you can!
Mia's in trouble!
I have to follow them
and bring her back!
[SATOU] My stamina is starting
to drain a little bit at a time.
Mia. Where is she?
[SATOU]
Huh?
Hmmm...
[SATOU]
Hmmm... Hmm...
I'm coming, Mia!
[ZEN]
No!
No! It's simply not possible!
How did you manage to escape
the abyss of my shadow prison?
Against the daunting oppression
of its endless nothingness,
you should
have been powerless!
[SATOU]
What a weirdo.
I can never tell if he's
shocked or impressed with me.
Well, I keep a small amulet.
So your magic doesn't work.
[ZEN] Trials must be
administered with fairness.
There are no grounds
for cheating.
Only someone who
has conquered the Cradle
should have the ability
to reach this room.
Those are the rules.
What're you, the game master?
[ZEN]
You insult me!
My Cradle is no game!
It is a formidable test!
Only a proper hero can conquer
its power and reach this room.
Only a hero with true
substance can do battle
with the Undead King!
[SATOU] Is he trying to say
I don't have the goods?
[ZEN laughs]
As long as I bear the
gift of God's blessing,
I can never perish
from this world.
[SATOU] I gotta get
Mia out of here fast.
[ZEN]
Nice try.
But if you want
to get to the end,
you must first start
at the beginning.
[sighs]
Oh boy. This sucks.
[ZEN]
You insult me!
My Cradle is no game!
It is a formidable test!
[SATOU] "The Cradle"? He shoulda
called it the "Big Ass Tree."
I'm guessing
Mia is somewhere inside.
Wow.
This place is right next to
Count Seiryuu's territory.
That's good news.
After I get to the
top and rescue Mia,
getting home won't
be a guessing game.
[SATOU]
What is this?
Looks like there's an
explanation in Elvish.
"Caution.
As this is an institute
for Elvish martial training,
the life support mechanisms
will only work on other elves.
There are no
restrictions upon whom
may enter the
training grounds.
But do so at your own peril.
The management here is
not responsible for any injury
or loss of property
incurred during use."
Weird. Hmm...
[sighs]
Going in is a risky move.
But Mia needs my help,
so I don't have a choice.
[SATOU]
Uh-oh.
Looks like I got company.
[SATOU]
This place is no joke.
There are 200 floors.
They're arranged
in groups of ten.
Every 20 floors,
a massive spiral staircase
stretches upward.
There are monsters stationed
in front of each access point
to the stairway.
If I had to guess, I'd bet they
get stronger the higher you get.
Compared to the Devil's
Labyrinth under Seiryuu City.
This Cradle feels a lot more
like a traditional
gaming experience.
It's crazy. It's exactly what
someone who's a fan of RPGs
for home consoles
would come up with.
In that case,
I should focus
on the first ten floors
and keep an eye
out for monsters.
[SATOU]
There.
Stop hiding and come out!
[DRYAD]
Shut up, you dum-dum!
[yawns]
I'm super annoyed because
I don't have enough MP!
[SATOU]
Perfect.
If I defeat her, she'll be
forced to open up a passageway
to the upper floors
and I'll get to the top faster.
If a classic dungeon crawler
fan designed this place,
there's bound to
be a portal setup
or a shortcut gimmick
around here somewhere.
Sorry, I'm too tired to fight.
I don't really see
how that's my problem.
[DRYAD groans]
Listen here, ya big jerk!
Back off or
I'll tell Toya on you!
Huh?
[SATOU]
Uh. Oh no.
Be mine forever, human!
Huh? I'm flattered,
but if you wanna propose,
you're gonna have
to wait 14 to 15 years.
I'm starving!
I want some food!
[SATOU] Hmm...
Well, I do have a little jerky.
Not human food, I want MP!
Right now!
[SATOU] Sorry,
but I need the MP for myself.
[DRYAD]
It only hurts for a little bit.
You'll feel much
better after, I swear!
Smooches!
I feel better!
[SATOU]
That wasn't your fault, Satou.
Think of it like a bee sting.
I don't want that title.
Can I give it back maybe?
[DRYAD] As thanks, I'll open
up the corridor for you!
It's all yours!
[SATOU]
Huh?
Trazayuya's room?
All righty then.
Here goes nothing.
Uh. Thank you?
[SATOU]
A laboratory?
I'm guessing this Trazayuya
character created the Cradle?
Is that who the Dryad
was talking about
when she said "Toya"?
[TRAZAYUYA] "We elves have such
a slight attachment to life.
When faced with life
or death situations,
strangely, we have
little will to struggle.
Because of that weakness,
many of our young have
died within the labyrinth.
The Cradle was
created for one purpose:
to instill in Elvenkind a
strong will to survive even
in the face of grave danger.
It seems that in
a hundred years,
no one has forgotten
about my greatest failure.
Soon, my long life
will come to an end at last.
As such, I will
seal this place away
until the day my
fellow elves find it useful.
[SATOU] I have faith
that elves will once again
lead the many
races of this world.
Trazayuya Bolenan."
[SATOU] He's of the same lineage
as Mia and the manager.
That's why this place needs her.
Well. Too bad.
Oh, joy.
Welcome back!
Hey.
I'm looking for
a little help here.
Is there a portal?
[DRYAD]
Sure is!
All you have to do is stand in
the middle of that fairy ring!
Where exactly do you wanna go?
The top floor.
I need to see the Cradle Master.
That's not gonna happen, buddy!
No way!
Fine, just send me up
as high as you can!
[DRYAD]
'Kay!
That'd be floor 100!
The Guardian Knight's Chamber!
Be careful.
The guardian on
that floor is pretty tough!
Thanks.
I'll be fine.
Here we go!
[spell chant]
[DRYAD]
Activate!
The marker is floor 100, the
Guardian Knight's Chamber.
[SATOU]
Huh?
[NUMBER 7]
Before we fight.
I need a moment please.
[SATOU] Aren't homunculi
supposed to be some sort
of artificial intelligence made
through the power of alchemy?
If that face is any indication,
I'm pretty sure these
models were based on Mia.
My congratulations on
making it this far, Voyager.
[SATOU] I guess she
doesn't know I cheated.
Thanks, but I'm just a merchant.
A merchant?
Brave Voyager.
Congratulations
on making it this far.
[SATOU]
I heard you before.
If you wish to continue onward,
you must first defeat
the mighty guardian
who protects these
chamber walls.
All victors will be
granted recompense
from our most noble
and gallant master.
[SATOU] I feel like I'm watching
an elementary school play.
Now approach, Iron Golem.
The battle commences!
Show him no mercy.
Number 7.
Number 6.
Use body strengthening
and split up.
We'll flank him on both sides.
[SATOU]
E. M. E. T. H.
Isn't that Hebrew?
[SATOU] It's just like in
the famous tale of the golem.
He figured out the
guardian's weakness!
This is why I suggested
we not leave
a conspicuous clue
written on his helmet!
Upon further reflection,
that does seem like
an obvious mistake.
[NUMBER 7]
Number 5 and Number 6!
I'll handle things here,
you two make a run
for it while you still can!
Oh, Number 7.
I swear, your bravery on this
day shall never be forgotten!
I concur with Number 5.
Only in lieu of the
phrase "make a run for it,"
I would say, "Commence retreat."
[SATOU] I guess the one with
side buns is the editor bot?
Fire! Strike! Now!
What am I supposed to do now?
I can't just gut
punch an A.I. lady
and leave her all on her own.
No. That's wrong.
So wrong.
There're all kinds of
weapons and potions here.
Pretty pricey stuff, too.
I'll help myself.
[NUMBER 7]
Master.
Sorry I failed you.
Master!
Oh, wow.
This looks like the
room the Dryad was in.
Maybe this'll help get her back
to one hundred percent again.
[DRYAD]
Water!
Now! Hand over the MP!
Aha!
You gave some to the other me
that was down below!
There's another you?
Yes, they're all me!
You humans are weird, the way
you're all separate individuals!
Plant and spirit folk like me?
We're all connected!
Though we lose contact
when we're low on MP!
[SATOU] Hey, would you
be willing to help me
get to the top?
Yeah! Sure!
Just give me one second!
[DRYAD]
Hmm?
It would seem the line
connecting us has been severed!
Sorry!
Right now you can only
get up to the 180th floor!
Oh, thanks.
That's great!
[DRYAD]
You got it, pal!
Oh, gross.
I think bugs ate
through the connection.
The next staircase is ahead.
Well, that was intense.
[ZEN] I never imagined
you would make it this far
in such a short period of time.
Same here.
I'll make you a deal, Skeletor.
Hand over the girl and you live.
[ZEN]
No.
You may have earned the right
to fight me by making it here.
But I'm afraid you lack the
credentials to face me.
If you truly wish to
claim the title of Hero,
there is one more challenge
you must overcome first:
You will fight
a dangerous enemy,
an enemy you have
no chance of defeating.
Your reward will be
this once lost,
ancient sword: Gjallarhorn!
Dangling a carrot
for me, are ya?
[ZEN]
Indeed.
If you were to hand over this
coveted sword to any king,
he would reward you
with glory beyond your
wildest imagination.
[SATOU] I can't figure out
what his angle is.
[ZEN] It's time for you
to meet your opponents,
Merchant Warrior.
[SATOU]
Seven homunculi.
I see two of the ones from
before, Numbers 5 and 6.
But where's Number 7?
She's not here.
[ZEN] A true Hero lives outside
the boundaries of safety.
He exists beyond the fine
line between life and death.
Thus, allow me to bestow you all
with God's miraculous blessing.
[SATOU]
Some kind of buff magic?
Oh no.
[ZEN] I do hope to see a
suitable battle to the death.
[SATOU]
Mia.