[ZEN] I do hope to see a
suitable battle to the death.
[SATOU]
Mia!
All right!
Activate!
[SATOU]
I don't get it.
Why fight so hard for a master
who treats you like pawns?
You're wrong.
We're not the pawns.
You are.
[SATOU]
This is not good.
One more.
[SATOU]
She has to know she can't win.
My master's wish.
Please make it
come true for him.
You must promise us this.
[ZEN]
Magnificent!
Truly magnificent!
Now you've earned the right
to be here, Mister Hero.
Mister Sorcerer.
Or wait.
Undead King.
Whoever you are.
You wanna tell me
about this wish?
[ZEN] It would be
my pleasure, young sir.
I wish to find a Hero who will
do me the service of killing me.
In my past life,
I met my end at the
hands of an unjust brutality.
God, in his wisdom, saw fit
to reincarnate me as an infant.
I was born into a highly
respectable family.
I even found a companion.
She was too good for me,
but I loved her dearly.
Life was good,
but I was a fool.
I naively believed my new life
would meet an entirely
different end from my last.
But unfortunately, God had
other plans in mind for me.
A noble fell in
love with my wife.
He imprisoned me and had me
executed on false pretenses.
He didn't stop there.
In the end, the heads of every
member of my family were strewn
about the castle grounds.
Among them,
the corpse of my wife,
cast aside like a rag doll,
like she was nothing.
[ZEN] I turned my wife and the
rest of my family into undead.
Hungry for sweet vengeance,
I bore my teeth
and unleashed holy hell on
the noble and his kinsman.
It was said they were
a resilient family,
but in the end, we prevailed.
Having accomplished my revenge,
I sought a means to end my life
and rejoin my
dearest wife in death.
But God's blessing would
not allow me to do so.
I tried everything,
even the power of Undead
and the Holy Sword,
but nothing worked.
After all,
God made me the
immortal King of Night.
He granted me a body
that would never die
and a soul that would
forever yearn for justice.
And the might to fight all
undue displays of power.
Now, "Hero,"
I have told you my story.
Before I fully descend
into the darkness,
use that sword
to strike me down!
My master has a wish.
Please make it come true.
[ZEN]
You have my gratitude, friend.
[laughs]
Darling!
My dearest love.
My sweetest one.
This time
we'll be together forever!
[VOICE A laughs]
What a failure!
[VOICE B]
Yes! A failure indeed!
[VOICE A]
Goodbye, Hero.
You win this time.
[laughs]
We'll meet again!
[VOICE B]
Goodbye!
What was that?
[ANNOUNCER]
System Message.
Please be advised,
the Cradle has begun its
self-destruct sequence.
For your own safety,
all staff and trainees are
advised to leave immediately.
I repeat.
System Message.
The Cradle has begun its
self-destruct sequence.
[ANNOUNCER]
For your own safety,
all staff and trainees...
[SATOU]
Mia, do you remember me?
[MIA]
Hmmm? Huh?
Don't worry, there's no
reason to be afraid anymore.
You're safe.
[ANNOUNCER]
System Message.
The Cradle has begun...
Hey.
Do you have any idea
how to turn that off?
[MIA]
I'll try.
I failed.
Jeez, you gave up fast!
Done!
[MIA]
We're safe?
Uh. Yeah.
Well, sort of.
We're not in the clear just yet.
It doesn't look like Zen ever
intended to sacrifice Mia.
He even has a clear
method of escape
built into the architecture
of the program.
But every other function
seems to be blocked out.
If I stick close to her,
in theory,
we should be able
to warp out together.
But wait.
What'll happen to
the homunculi if I leave?
Number 7 is still on
one of the bottom floors.
I can't just abandon her!
Mia. Listen to me.
There's someone down
below who needs my help.
It's not safe!
Don't worry, I'm not gonna die!
I promise.
A promise is a promise, Satou.
So no matter what, you'd better
come back here alive!
I'll make it back,
you have my word!
I better move.
I have a promise to keep!
Huh?
There!
Salty!
Is this place turning into salt?
There! Number 7!
Green Girl!
You rang?
[SATOU] I need you to transport
us outside the tree, stat!
I think I can
establish a connection
and get you near the bottom,
but I'm gonna need
you to load me up
with delicious seeds first!
Just seeds?
You don't care which kind?
Nope!
As long as it's plant seed,
it'll do the trick!
[SATOU]
Here. Is this enough?
No dum-dum, not even close.
For this to work, I'll need
three times what I got before.
You won't have any MP left.
[SATOU]
Whatever! It's fine!
Yay!
[DRYAN]
Smooches!
Ahhh...
I'm synched and ready to roll!
Well!
Let's go!
Thanks a lot.
Oh, it was my pleasure,
and that MP really hit the spot.
Well, Hero Man.
You'd better bolt!
[SATOU]
Bolt?
It's a tidal wave of salt!
Quick! Run!
Oh no, I'm safe.
As long as there
are trees I'm okay!
Thank you.
Good luck.
I need to activate
the transport skill
I haven't even touched yet.
It's much easier to run now!
But I'm not running fast enough!
Come on, Satou.
Think fast!
[gasps]
Water?
A lake or a bog?
Doesn't matter.
It's likely the only
chance I've got!
I need to break the waves.
But how?
I know!
A wall!
The kettle's really mad at us!
[POCHI]
The kettle man is super scary!
[SATOU] What does that
have to do with anything?
Come on, Satou get
your head in the game!
If I had some kind
of Earth Magic
instead of this useless Fire
Shot, then I could make a wall!
But, is it useless?
Water gets one thousand
times bigger when it boils.
[SATOU]
No.
It's not useless at all!
Okay. Here goes!
Here we go!
[roars]
Ahh!
[POCHI]
He's back!
[LIZA sobs]
Master!
[TAMA]
You didn't die!
[POCHI]
We're so happy!
[SATOU]
So am I.
You have no idea.
[POCHI]
We were really worried, Master!
[TAMA]
No scratches?
[LULU]
Welcome back, sir.
[ZEN]
Thank you, son.
If the reincarnated girl
with whom you travel
is truly precious to you,
have her exercise caution
and restraint in using the
God-given power she wields.
It is too much for
any mortal to bear.
Do not let her meet
the same fate as I.
Huh?
I was so worried about you.
Promise me you'll never do
anything crazy like that again!
'Kay.
Promise.
[ARISA cries]
Girls.
Please.
I'm okay.
Hey.
Well.
It's done.
You kept your word.
Yeah. Of course.
Satou.
Hear this:
[MIA] A descendant
of the Bolenan family,
I'm the youngest elf
in the Bolenan Forest.
I come from a distinguished
line of proud elves.
On behalf of all of them,
I wish to tell you this:
You have our sincere gratitude.
[NUMBER 1]
Satou, sir.
Not only did you
spare all of our lives,
even after we
tried to take yours.
But you ran back into harm's way
in order to rescue
Number 7 from certain death.
We cannot thank
you enough for this!
Tell me.
Where's Master?
Well, your master passed on.
[NUMBER 1]
Master Satou.
You have our allegiance.
As your new subjects, we will
obey your every command!
Uh! Hang on a sec!
Before we can fulfill
our duty to serve you.
There is a task that
we must first complete.
It's our master Zen's
wedding ring.
Will you allow us to take it
to his wife's resting place?
[SATOU] Oh. Take as
much time as you need.
Thank you, sir.
But one of must stay behind.
Please.
Pick the number
you'd like to keep.
[SATOU]
You should all go.
That's totally cool with me.
No, sir.
We will never leave you alone.
Cool. I'll let you
make that call then.
[NUMBERS]
Fight!
Ro. Sham. Bo! Ro. Sham. Bo!
Ro. Sham. Bo!
[SATOU]
This is super weird.
--[NUMBER 1, 2] Paper!
--[NUMBER 7] Scissors!
Master, I very
much look forward
to the pleasure of
remaining by your side.
[SATOU]
Great.
Thanks.
You're 7, right?
Can I maybe give you
a different name instead?
[NUMBER 7]
Yes.
[SATOU]
Then, welcome to the team.
Nana.
Yes. Master.
[MIA]
Yuya.
[YUSARATOYA]
Mia.
[MIA]
I'll stay, too.
[YUSARATOYA]
You can't.
[MIA]
I can.
[YUSARATOYA]
But how?
[MIA]
With Satou.
[YUSARATOYA]
Makes sense.
[SATOU] No one would
be mad at you two
for using longer sentences.
[THORN]
I see.
A mysterious necromancer
with a vendetta against
the Shiga Kingdom, huh?
Yep.
That's what the brave men
who rescued me said.
I'm a lucky guy.
Welp, that's a flat-out lie.
Oh! You've come back!
Are you all right, Satou?
[SATOU]
Yes, I'm fine.
Sorry to make you worry.
[ZENA sobs]
[ZENA] When I heard you
were taken, I was horrified.
All I could do was think
of ways to bring you home!
But you're safe and sound.
That's what matters now.
Yeah.
I'm just sorry the whole
ordeal made you so upset.
Oh yeah!
Can't believe I almost forgot.
I bought a little
something, just for you.
Are these...?
What a romantic gift!
[SATOU]
Zena.
Yes? What?
[SATOU]
Well, uh... The thing is...
The elf girl who was kidnapped
needs someone to take her home
where she belongs,
so I volunteered for the job.
[gasps]
[ZENA]
You're going to the elf village?
[SATOU] It's to the southeast
of the Shiga Kingdom.
[ZENA]
Tell me the truth, Satou:
Do you ever intend to
return to Seiryuu City?
Yes, of course I do.
[ZENA]
Thank goodness.
[SATOU]
And when I do get back?
I'll have a million stories to
tell you about my crazy journey.
I can promise you that.
Right.
It's a promise, then.
Well, Master!
We are ready to
depart when you are!
Hooray!
We can't wait!
I'm here.
Please accept
my apologies, Satou.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to
find you a proper house.
[SATOU]
It's cool.
Hey, you helped me buy this
cart, and that's no small thing.
Watch over Mia.
[SATOU]
I will.
I promise.
Be careful out there.
The roads are crawling
with bandits
and lots of shady rogues.
[YUNI]
Hang on!
Here.
I wanted to give you your gifts!
These look really good!
We're both starving, too!
Can't wait to dig in!
No, don't eat it.
It's a necklace.
[POCHI]
Oh! Really?
[TAMA]
That's disappointing.
[POCHI]
But it looks so delicious!
[ZENA]
Satou, wait!
[SATOU]
Zena?
[ZENA]
Glad I wasn't too late.
Yeah, me too.
I was hoping we'd
get a proper goodbye.
[ZENA] There's something
I need to say to you.
Satou.
You're so great, and I wish
that I could come with you.
But I can't just
abandon my family.
I love them, too.
I want to join you. I do.
But I just can't.
That said, this spring,
my brother will officially
become the head of our family.
I've spoken to him,
and as far as he's concerned,
I'm free to do as I like.
And so,
I have good news.
[ZENA] When Spring comes,
I'll be able to join you!
[ARISA]
Don't look so blue, Master.
I know you'll miss Zena,
but at least you've got us.
Does your tummy hurt?
Are you gonna throw up?
Satou?
I'll be all right.
Sir.
I read in one of my
old master's code libraries
that crying into a woman's
chest will make you feel better!
Hey! No. Fair!
Cut that out right now!
Lulu, do something!
Quick!
[LULU]
No, Arisa.
I'm driving the cart.
I have to focus on the road.
[VOICE B]
Don't forget.
We'll be together.
Forever.