[SATOU] I guess they don't get
skills just by being with me.
There're no changes on
their experience bars.
Huh.
Tama.
Go find us some stones
about the size of a core!
'Kay!
There's a bug up ahead!
I got him!
Tama!
Let it rip!
Yeah!
Pochi, Tama, get back a bit!
Liza, when you see an
opening, stab him in the gut!
Right!
Liza, Tama.
Now you go retrieve the core!
And Pochi, you come with me!
There're more bugs up ahead!
Jeez.
That's a lot of rocks.
Pochi.
Take the rocks and
throw them at the bug's side.
But stay on the move,
and then try to hide somewhere.
Right.
Okie-dokie.
Huh?
[POCHI]
Liza! Tama!
Don't let the big
nasty bug eat me...
[SATOU]
Pochi! Wait! Come back!
[screams]
That wasn't part of the plan.
Is Pochi all right?
What's wrong?
Is she hurt?
Oh, no, she's okay.
She just got scared, that's all.
We should get going.
[POCHI]
I'm so sorry, Master.
[SATOU]
I'm not mad at her.
I'm just worried
she's gonna get hurt
if she freaks out like that.
Pochi,
when things get dicey,
it's okay to run away sometimes.
But you still gotta
keep a cool head.
Understand?
Right. Okie-doke.
[SATOU]
I don't like "tamer."
If it were up to me,
I'd go with "patient educator."
[SATOU] Awesome! Their
levels are starting to go up!
I guess you get
skills automatically
when your level increases.
Master, we're finished.
We've collected
all of the cores.
[SATOU]
Cool.
Huh.
She's not calling me
"Young Master" anymore.
Is it weird if I say I miss it?
[SATOUR] She doesn't
have much stamina left.
Hey!
I think we should take a break.
What kind of food do we have?
Oh wow!
This is really good!
It's the best!
Meat is the greatest food ever!
[LIZA] When you bite into
the succulent, tender jerky
the flavors explode in
your mouth like canon fire!
[SATOU] When you're done eating,
you should get some sleep.
Would you like me
to set up camp, Master?
[SATOU]
Hmm...
No, just get some rest.
Hey! Awesome job!
Right!
--Yay!
--Thank you!
[SATOU] It's the first time
I've let them take the reigns.
But they handled
it like old pros.
[LIZA]
Master.
I want to start a fire.
Is that all right?
Why a fire?
[LIZA] Well, I was
thinking I would like
to prepare some frog meat.
Forgive me.
There's no need to
forgive you, but, "frog meat"?
[LIZA]
It's quite delicious.
But if not cooked properly,
we could fall deathly ill.
Okay, why not?
[LIZA]
Here, Master.
[SATOU]
Oh, wow.
Thanks.
I hope I don't puke.
Not bad.
It tastes like chicken.
Probably because of the
seasoning salt she used.
Huh? Why aren't
they chowing down?
Please, don't wait for me.
If I were you,
I'd go ahead and dig
in while the frog's still hot.
Hot meat!
Piping hot!
[SATOU sighs]
If we keep this pace up,
we'll find our way out
of this crazy labyrinth
in no time at all.
But once we do,
what happens to them?
Here goes nothing.
Fire Ball Attack!
Uh-oh.
I guess that fire shot spell
isn't gonna get the job done
against a level 10 slime.
[LIZA]
If I may,
the most effective way to
defeat a purple slime monster
is to penetrate its core.
It works every single time.
Slime. Gross.
It turned into
a puddle of nasty.
Huh? That wall is weird.
[SATOU]
A hidden door?
Or a trap?
[gasps]
Get back now.
A Level 40 beast?
Master, no!
Oh dear!
Please be careful!
All right!
Nice job!
Way to go, Master!
[SATOU] Good thing "trap
setting" was one of my skills.
[TAMA]
Sticky, sticky.
[POCHI]
My feet are stuck in the goo.
There are people
in those things.
We have to save them.
[JIN]
Bless you, my son.
I am the head viscount of
the ancient Belton Family.
I am know as Jin Belton.
You have my thanks.
For your gallantry, I'll see
you receive a handsome reward.
[NIDOREN] Thank you so much
for rescuing me, my friends.
The name is Nidoren.
I am a slave trader.
I'm Satou,
and I've just recently become
a professional merchant.
[VILLAGER B]
Take your hands off me!
Give me the dagger, you beast!
[SATOU]
Hold on.
I remember him.
Eh! Sorry, I can't.
This blade is my master's.
You can't have it.
Such insolence!
I'll beat it right outta ya!
Pochi. Come here, please.
[POCHI]
Right. Okie-dokie.
Hey! Cut me loose, will ya?
Actually, I'm a
little busy right now.
Find your own way, pal.
What is this,
some kind of a joke?
C'mon, you can't
just leave me here!
[JIN]
That's enough.
You keep yelling like that,
you'll attract
unwanted attention.
So shut your trap
or I'll burn you
to cinders and let the
monsters eat your bones.
[fighting sounds]
I hear fighting!
There's a battle just
down this corridor, Master!
We'll go ahead and
see what's happening.
Follow slightly behind us
and make sure nothing tries
to attack from the rear.
Tama! Pochi! I need a torch!
--Meow!
--Okay!
Distract the slime monsters
and try to lure them
away from the troops!
Liza, aim for the cores
and take them out!
Once they're dead,
I want you to run back here
as fast as you can, okay?
[GIRLS agree]
I'm a hundred times stronger
than those stupid
little demi-freaks!
As long as I have this
sword, I'll be just fine!
[roars]
We showed them who's boss!
Darn right we did!
Excellent job, ladies.
Huh...?
[SATOU]
Zena!
Are you okay?
It really is you!
Huh?
Oh, Satou!
I was so worried about you!
[ORNA]
Zena.
This isn't the time
to celebrate.
I think it's best we take care
of the monsters first.
[ZENA]
Priestess Orna.
[ORNA] Judging by
what I've just witnessed,
I take it you've determined
where the slime monsters'
weakness lies.
Yes.
All you have to do is
penetrate their cores,
and they disintegrate.
How'd you figure
that out, Satou?
You're so smart.
No. Liza is the
smart one, not me.
Who?
Is Liza your girlfriend?
Ask if he's been
unfaithful later, dear.
[SATOU]
Unfaithful?
Oh, I get it.
She doesn't
understand who Liza is.
Well, I'm just happy
you're safe, Satou.
Yeah, these three are the
only reason I'm safe at all.
[ZENA]
Oh!
You mean the
demi-humans from before.
[POCHI]
My name's Pochi and this is...
[TAMA]
...Tama.
[SATOU]
Huh.
I didn't know they were so shy.
[LIZA]
My name is Liza.
You saved us from
being stoned to death.
We are in your debt.
You're nice!
Like really, really nice!
Heh! You're nice, too.
[TAMA]
Huh?
Master, that wall.
It's weird, too.
[SATOU]
Another hidden door.
And it looks like
it's right above the spot
where we defeated
that undead beast.
Good work, Tama.
[SOLDIER A]
Look. It's a treasure box!
[SOLDIER B]
Back off, it's mine!
I found it!
[DEMON]
Ha! I'm back!
[DEMON] I didn't think
so many of you would come!
The more the merrier!
I'd say this labyrinth
just got a lot less cool!
[SOLDIER C]
Everyone, take your positions!
Attack from all sides!
But be careful:
This demon can use magic!
Viscount, provide defensive
cover for the men in front!
You made a mistake, demon!
You should've stayed
hidden inside of your chest.
You can't fend off
my fire magic.
So I'll use Blast Pole!
[DEMON laughs]
Human spells are so slow!
I'm bored out of my mind!
[SATOU]
What is this sensation?
Huh?
I've never seen
anything like this!
Would you look
at all of that meat?
There's enough to feed an army!
Pochi, Tama!
Let's gather as much food
for Master as we possibly can!
[SATOU]
What the hell is going on?
Do the soldiers look like
roast chicken to them?
I need to snap them
out of this fast!
[DEMON]
You humans are such fools!
I'll watch with delight as
you rip each other to shreds!
Demon.
If you think we're going
to let you defeat us
without putting up a fight,
then the only fool here is you!
Blast Pole!
[DEMON laughs]
[gasps]
What? No way!
Mid-level magic doesn't work?
[DEMON]
Don't you know demons love heat?
Better try another spell!
[SATOU] Guess he's using
some kind of protection magic.
All right, Satou!
Time to get in the fight!
[SATOU]
Damn it.
Oh, yeah.
Satou!
[SATOU]
Come on, beast.
Satou, no!
That's it!
Wow. This holy sword
is crazy sharp.
I took damage
when I pulled it out.
I guess I should
leave it unequipped.
Meantime...
[DEMON]
Fight back if you like!
But you'll never prevail!
[DEMON]
Ow!
[SATOU]
Stand down, knights.
I'll take care of
this demon freak.
Flame Spear Attack!
Sacred Javelin!
[DEMON]
Who the hell are you?
You're freakishly strong!
Where did Master go?
Is he gone?
No, I can still smell him.
[SATOU] I need to make
sure they don't notice.
[DEMON]
Human!
Who are you?
No one damages a
demon by throwing rocks!
I am confused and enraged!
I'm going to be bested
by a human being!
How can this be happening?
It's not possible!
[SATOU]
I'll finish him off.
Damn it!
[DEMON]
My master!
How I've longed
to see thee once again?
Kneel before my master,
the godlike Demon Lord!
He is part of the
Demon King's innermost circle!
[JIN]
This is bad news.
A high-level demon lord!
[DEMON LORD]
In setting up this labyrinth
and summoning me hither,
you have done well.
Here is your reward.
[DEMON] I get to become one
with my master once again!
I am beyond overjoyed!
[DEMON LORD]
Run away, my little ants!
Those who are strong,
stand firm and prepare to fight!
I will test your mettle!
[SATOU]
That should take care of them.
[DEMON LORD] I did not realize
a hero would be present.
Did you have a
divine revelation?
No matter, you will fall.
Try as you might,
you will never defeat me!
[SATOU] Just how much are you
going to strengthen yourself?
[ZENA] But they say if the sword
accepts the person holding it,
the blade will still glow.
[DEMON LORD]
What's ails you, Hero?
Do you not know how
to use your holy sword?
Such a pity.
[DEMON LORD]
You're quite durable.
Consider me mildly impressed.
[SATOU]
That was close.
If the holy sword won't work,
then I'll have to use magic.
But low-end magic like
Fire Shot isn't going to work.
What about meteor shower?
No, I can't use that.
Air Hammer!
Flame Spear attack!
Sacred Javelin Attack!
[DEMON LORD]
You're interrupting my fun
with your infantile spells!
Now you've angered me,
you human scum!
[SATOU]
Take this!
[DEMON LORD]
It seems I was over-confident!
[ZENA] It is quite
difficult to fight demons
because only magic
and magical weaponry
can defeat them.
[SATOU]
All right.
[DEMON LORD] Did you truly
think I wouldn't notice
you abandoned your holy sword?
You cannot fool me.
[SATOU]
Fire Shot!
Did it work?
[DEMON LORD] I didn't
think someone so skilled
at martial arts could
utilize magic, too.
I don't understand!
How is this happening?
My word.
That has to be the high-level
magic, Crimson Javelin!
[SATOU] Well, actually, no, it's
the starting magic: Fire Shot.
That's right.
The magic gauge on Meteor
Shower said it had ten times
the original power.
Speaking of which,
that reminds me.
In order to defeat a Demon Lord,
a hero must wield a holy sword.
[SATOU]
Demon Lords aren't anything like
that eyeball weirdo.
They're godlike entities!
Even though I have a holy sword,
I don't have the
title of "hero" yet.
That's why I can't
get a good hit in.
[SATOU]
But is that right?
Hold on.
What titles do I already have?
[SATOU] If wielding a holy sword
as a "Hero" makes it possible
to smite a godlike entity!
[SATOU] Then it stands to
reason: wielding a Divine Sword
as a "God-killer" should
achieve the exact same result!
[DEMON LORD]
What is that blade in your hand?
Damn you, human.
I am vanquished.
[TAMA]
Master!
You did it!
You beat the Demon Lord!
Pardon me, friend,
are you, Satou?
[SATOU]
Yes, I am.
[SOLDIER F]
Are these your slaves?
[SATOU]
Yes.
Well, no, not officially.
Fine.
Well, there's someone
looking for you.
Come on.
[SATOU]
Uh, all right.
Ladies.
Are you coming?
Okay!
[VILLAGER B]
Hey.
I was wrong
to mistreat you, girls.
I hope you'll forgive me.
[ZENA]
Satou!
You have no idea
how worried I was!
[SATOU]
Well, the important thing is:
We're both safe and sound now!
[SATOU]
I'm wracking up new titles.
But to be honest,
out of all of them, this is
the one I care about the most.
Mr. Satou,
I hereby proclaim these
slaves are officially yours!
--[TAMA] Victory!
--[POCHI] Now we're master's!
I thought you
might like to know,
there are several slaves
who didn't sell today.
I'd be happy if you took a look.
[SATOU]
No, thanks.
I think I'm all
stocked up on that front.
[LULU]
Uh.
My name is Lulu, sir.
[SATOU]
Lulu.
She seems nice.
[ARISA]
Hello. My name is Arisa.
Satou-sama.
I'm yours.
[SATOU gasps]
What?