[ARISA]
Hello. My name is Arisa.
Satou-sama.
[SATOU]
She used the honorific!
Is this girl Japanese?
I have an idea.
[gasps]
Huh?
[ARISA screams]
Get it off!
Disgusting!
I hate spiders more
than anything else
in the entire world!
[SATOU]
Thought so.
[MALE VILLAGER A]
Step right up, folks!
[sighs]
[SATOU]
I bought both of them.
I'm such a sucker.
There's a "kumo" in your hair.
[SATOU]
I knew she was from Japan.
Japanese girls
always hate spiders.
[ARISA]
Like I said, my name is Arisa.
It's been well over a decade
since I was born into the
mysterious Kingdom of Kuvork.
I hope you'll treat me with
love and respect, Master.
[LULU]
I'm Lulu.
I'm 14.
I'm from the Kingdom of Kuvork.
As you can see,
I'm homely, weak and shy, too.
But I am sturdy as a pack horse.
So please don't cast me aside.
It's nice to meet you both.
I'm Satou.
[POCHI]
My name is Pochi.
[TAMA]
Tama.
Greetings, my name is Liza.
A spawn of the Orangescale race.
My village was toppled
by the Weaselmen.
Shortly after,
I was sold as a slave.
But I am very proud to have
been sold to the Shiga Kingdom.
Hey.
Too much.
[LIZA]
Oh!
I am terribly sorry!
An odd-eared race and a slave?
I'll admit, I've never met
anyone quite like you before.
[SATOU]
Yeah. They're unique for sure.
[LIZA]
They're kind souls.
Be patient with them.
Aww!
How could I not be patient with
two little cuties like them?
Are we little cuties?
[ARISA]
Mm-hmm.
You are really cute, Tama!
[TAMA]
So are you, Pochi!
[giggling]
[ARISA]
Nice to meet you.
[LULU]
Yes, nice to meet you girls.
[POCHI]
Yes! The pleasure is ours!
[TAMA]
What she said!
[LIZA]
We're glad to have you with us.
You're all so lovely!
[SATOU]
She doesn't hate demi-humans.
What a relief.
Well, why don't we
head back to the inn?
[GIRLS agree]
Wanna hold hands?
We already are
holding hands, silly!
[SATOU]
Arisa's from Japan for sure.
But I shouldn't talk about
it in front of the others.
[LULU's stomach growls]
[SATOU]
Something sure does smell good.
Let's grab some food
before we go home.
What do you guys want?
Meat! Meat!
Yeah! Meat sounds great!
We will eat
anything you offer us
with a smile on our face
and gratitude in our hearts.
But if I must choose,
then I select poultry
of the chicken variety.
[SATOU] Aren't birds
and lizards relatives?
I'm a bit confused, Master.
As slaves, we aren't supposed to
be particular about what we eat.
[LULU's stomach growls]
[SATOU chuckles]
I'm curious, what type of
food did you normally get?
We never had a say
in the matter really.
They usually
gave us stale bread.
Day-old soup without any
meat was considered a feast!
We were lucky if we
received one meal a day.
When they didn't feed us,
we would forage for
fruits, berries, and twigs.
One time?
I had no choice but
to eat a leaf for breakfast.
Acorn nuts!
And weeds!
[SATOU]
Wait.
Are you serious?
Well, at least
her tail is excited.
All right, dig in!
Bless this food.
Bless our food, too.
Wow. It's super hot!
Uh.
You might wanna
blow on it first.
Right. Okies!
[TAMA]
'Kay.
It's like my mouth's on fire.
[TAMA]
Chewy, chewy.
[LIZA]
It's quite tasty.
[POCHI]
And it's really crunchy, too!
[SATOU] Hmm...
It's a little on the salty side.
But it's not bad.
It seems like there're a lotta
manual laborers around here.
Maybe this is the
kinda stuff they like?
Food made with entrails
is generally supposed
to have a variety of
textures and flavors,
but there are some
people who have trouble
with the unique aroma.
I don't know if they were
just meticulous in preparing it,
or if there's something
unique about the vegetables
it was simmered with,
but this stuff smells great!
Would you like to
try some of this, kid?
[SATOU] Wow! This is
just like tecchanyaki!
And this must be
heart with liver.
Ah! Yikes! It's so spicy!
Spicy-spice!
This is hotter than a
Weaselman on the trail
of an Orangescale.
Easy, girls.
If it's too hot don't
force yourselves.
Whatever you don't want,
I'll eat myself.
Here you go.
[TAMA]
Thanks a lot.
[POCHI]
You're so sweet!
[ARISA]
Let's dig in.
[LULU]
Please, enjoy.
[LIZA]
Where are you going, Master?
I won't be gone too long.
I just want to do
a little shopping
in the neighborhood is all.
Oh!
In that case, let me help!
No. Eat up. Please.
That's an order, ladies.
[SATOU]
Huh. That's right.
Liza said she
was hungry for chicken.
I think I'll buy
her a midnight snack.
Hungry?
Umm. Eat?
Make sure that you share it
with your friends, okay?
[ARISA]
Well? What do you think?
You look awesome!
You have quite the eye
for fashion, Master.
We're cute!
We look super-duper great!
[MARTHA]
Hey, Satou!
How are you, Martha?
Miss Marientail told me
all about your adventures.
It was quite a yarn.
Your room is still as it was,
so you're welcome to rest up,
but...
...it appears you might
need a little more space.
[SATOU]
Yes. These are my friends.
Without their help, I couldn't
have escaped the labyrinth.
[ARISA]
The labyrinth?
Actually, I was hoping I could
get a few extra rooms for them.
Is there space?
[MOSA]
I'm sorry.
But we're all booked up, dear.
[SATOU]
Demi-human haters.
Martha, will you take those
two to my room please?
The rest of us'll just have
to camp outside tonight.
Oh. Master.
You are such a generous soul.
Don't look so mad.
You're likely to frighten us
to the core with those
mean old scowls.
Ma'am?
If it's all right by you,
I was hoping we might use your
shed or a stable for the night?
These girls saved
countless human lives
while braving the darkness
and terror of the labyrinth.
Though they will
receive no medals
for their display of courage,
perhaps you can spare
them a little mercy?
A person's good deeds should
always be paid back in kind.
Oh. Yes.
That's an excellent point.
The shed is chalk
full to the brim.
But the stable has
more than enough room.
I do hope I was helpful, Master.
Yeah, you were.
Thank you for that.
All right.
I think this blanket will
keep you from getting needled
by the hay in your sleep.
[TAMA]
Fluffy-fluff!
[SATOU]
Why did I get "needlework"?
Oh well, maybe it'll
come in handy one day.
If any troublemakers
try to bother you.
Don't kill 'em unless
you have no choice.
If you need help, just shout.
I'll come running
here first thing.
Right. Understood.
Aye-aye!
Okie-dokies!
There's no need for that.
Just take care
of yourself, okay?
Yes. Right.
Oh, no, are you hurt?
No! I'm perfectly fine.
Thank you so much
for asking, Master!
[SATOU] I think Lulu's a bit
uncomfortable around men.
[ARISA]
We're ready for you, Master.
[SATOU]
Oh, no.
Are they serious?
Are they nudists?
Is that a thing here?
Ladies, the covers are
a bit on the thin side.
You'll catch a cold like that.
Put something on, please.
Oh. But... our services?
[SATOU]
Uhh.
If she means what
I think she means,
and I'm pretty sure she does?
Yikes.
I'm not interested in that.
'Scuse me?
We've got a big day
tomorrow of shopping
and stocking up on supplies.
So get some rest.
It's okay.
Those days are
all in the past now.
Huh?
[ARISA giggles]
Well, hello.
Did I wake you up?
[ARISA giggles]
Whoops, I stole a little kiss.
[SATOU]
Hold on.
She wasn't in my bed
when I fell asleep.
My mind is telling me no.
But my body?
My body's telling me yes.
Wait!
Since when am I a pedophile?
It's like I'm being compelled
to do this against my will!
That's it!
[ARISA giggles]
Arisa.
No more using magic, understood?
That's an order.
[gasps]
And one more thing!
Any magic or skills
you've already activated
are to be released at once!
You hear me?
That is an order!
[sighs]
[ARISA]
No fair.
[SATOU]
Hmm?
No fair?
It's the second time you've
used psychic magic tonight.
First, you used it on the
other guests at the inn.
Probably some trick to
neutralize their disdain
for Pochi and the others.
And these are the three spells
you were using to manipulate me?
Why were you trying to control
me by using a psychic spell?
I don't know what
you're asking me, Master.
Look, from now on,
no more avoiding
the subject either.
Tell me what you
were doing, Arisa.
Might as well see
how effective this is.
I'm going to ask
you one more time.
What were you doing?
I only wanted to
service you, Master.
You have my word.
I still don't understand.
Could you try and
explain it more clearly?
Oh, come on!
What could be clearer than that?
I fell for you the moment
I first laid eyes on you!
Uh...
"Fell for me"?
[ARISA]
Your fine, soft, black hair!
Your easygoing attitude!
Your cute baby face!
Your skinny build!
Your smooth skin with no hair
where there shouldn't be!
All I've ever wanted is
to marry someone like you!
But alas, the perfect man,
the man I've always
dreamed I'd find,
is my master, and he commands
me not to service him!
How can I accept that?
That's why I used a spell.
And if that makes
you angry with me!
Oh well!
So when I didn't
fall for you right away,
you decided to brainwash me?
You make it sound so wrong!
It's the duty of a slave girl
to seduce her master
and do everything she
can to make him feel good!
[SATOU]
That is not right.
I understand.
At least, I think.
I was waiting for you
to come call on me,
but you fell asleep.
That made me unhappy.
So I decided the next best
thing was to crawl in bed
and watch you sleep.
I'm so naughty.
Oops.
[SATOU] You were feeling amorous
and you decided to act on it.
More or less.
[SATOU]
Ugh... Good grief.
She is a hot mess.
I've never seen
these skills before.
Haha.
My name's Tachibana Arisa,
and I'm from Japan,
just like you.
[SATOU]
I knew it.
[ARISA]
Well, I was from Japan.
I was reincarnated
in the Kuvork Kingdom.
Strangely, I still
have my memories
from my former life on earth.
Were you reincarnated too?
Wait, what?
I get it.
With soft, smooth,
black hair like that,
I'm guessing you were
summoned here as a hero.
Weren't you, Master?
Look at that, you've
just clammed up.
You're only the second
Japanese person I've met here.
Did you know that?
[SATOU] Wait. Does that
mean Lulu's the other one?
Oh no. Not Lulu.
Although, apparently, her
grandfather was Japanese.
Fate is cruel, is it not?
If she'd been born in Japan,
she could've become a teen idol.
Wait. An idol?
Unfortunately, the people here
don't find her
attractive in the least.
Now, getting back to
the original question.
Were you reincarnated in this
world or are you a transfer?
Truth is, I don't know.
Well.
Maybe I can help!
Tell me: What makes
a transfer different?
[ARISA] People who are
reincarnated in this world
are those who died
in our old world.
People who are transported here
are compelled to appear
in this world as a result
of summoning magic.
They're either summoned
heroes or reincarnations.
So when you're reincarnated,
do you start as a baby?
Yes, in this world,
that's precisely how it works.
[SATOU]
Do people who are transported
keep their original appearance?
Do they look
exactly like they did
before they were transferred?
As far as I know,
when they appear,
they're even wearing the same
clothes they that wore on earth.
And guess what?
Their features
stay the same too--
[SATOU]
Hmm...
[SATOU] I don't think
either applies to me then.
Are you saying you
didn't meet God, Satou?
[SATOU]
God?
No, I didn't.
[ARISA]
Oh.
Well, tell me this:
Were you inside a summoner's
circle when you appeared?
[SATOU] No, I was alone
in the wasteland.
[ARISA]
I see.
Did you start out
at a high level?
Like with infinite MP?
And a whole bunch
of crazy skills?
I started at
level one, actually.
My MP was zero.
No skills either.
Wait.
I had those disposable
meteor shower icons.
That's no fun.
Good luck beating
a dumb game like that.
[SATOU]
Hmm...
Uh. So... one question.
Sure, I don't mind telling you!
My bra size is--
[SATOU]
This isn't an order.
So if you don't want to
answer that's totally okay.
Can you tell me how
you became a slave?
[MARTHA]
Satou, are you awake?
Look! Your girlfriend is here!
Oh! No, we're not--
Hey. What's up?
Sorry for the mess, things
have been a little nuts here.
I should put a shirt on.
[MARTHA]
Ooo.
Your boyfriend's
got a nice bod--
[gasps]
Oh, Master.
You're scaring me a little.
Please don't hurt me.
You creep.
How could you treat young
girls like objects, Satou?
How could you?
Well, good luck with that.
[yawns]
Aren't you going after her?
I definitely don't
recommend putting it off.
[SATOU]
Zena and I are just friends,
but still, this looks bad.
Please.
Don't be upset.
[ZENA]
I'm not upset.
I'm disappointed!
You were sleeping
with that little girl!
[SATOU] She crawled into my
bed when she was half asleep.
Oh. She did?
But Lilio told me that
men only buy slaves
to satisfy their insatiable
carnal appetites!
[SATOU]
Damn, Lilio!
Look, Zena.
I know some guys are like that,
but I swear, I'm not.
I just bought them cause I
needed help with the day to day.
Oh. You're telling the truth?
[SATOU] I don't know what it is,
but you look different today.
Your clothes are frillier.
There's a new kind of
elegance to your style.
I guess what I mean is,
you look really pretty.
When your back's
against the wall,
shower them
with compliments.
Thank you.
That's very sweet.
[SATOU]
Hey, Zena!
There's a store around here that
sells the most beautiful shawls!
You wanna go check it out?
I think they'd
look great on you.
[ZENA]
Oh, Satou.
That would be lovely!
[chuckles]
[ARISA]
There you are!
Welcome home!
I'm very glad to
see all is well again!
[SATOU] Does she
not realize she's the one
who caused the
freakin' problem?
Ow!
Yeah, I'm back.
Go get the others, will ya?
Right!
[SATOU] Can you tell me
how you became a slave?
That story is not a simple one.
When I got here, I tried
to help the country I ruled
using memories
from my former life.
At first things went
smoothly enough.
But then it all took a
sudden turn for the worse.
Conflict started to break out.
In the end, a neighboring
country took over.
[SATOU]
Was someone behind it?
[ARISA]
Yes.
I didn't find out who
till much later, though.
At the time, I was depressed,
but I chalked it up
to the differences between
this world and earth.
After our country was conquered,
they publicly executed the king,
the crown prince,
their consorts,
and a slew of loyal subjects
in order to quell dissent.
And then,
they ordered the mages
to force us into slavery.
We were all on our own without a
soul in the world to protect us.
Then one day, out of nowhere,
a demon appeared.
The demon attacked,
toppling both the castle and the
surrounding villages as well.
Everything was
engulfed in flames.
So Lulu and I ran to
the mountains for cover.
We had no food.
We were starving
and close to death.
And that's when that slave
trader, Nidoren, picked us up.
Lulu wasn't feeling well,
so I let her stay in the room.
I hope that's all right?
Thank you for letting me know.
Not a problem.
Here, use this money
to buy clothes
and daily necessities
for the entire crew.
I'll let you be in
charge of negotiations.
Consider it done, Master!
[SATOU]
Liza, watch Arisa's back.
Be on the lookout
for pickpockets, okay?
Yes.
I can keep her safe too!
So can I!
[SATOU]
Fine.
You two watch her flanks and
make sure she isn't ambushed.
Can I pretty please
use local security magic
and concealment skills
if I run into trouble?
I forgot that I shut that down.
Permission granted.
Thank you, Master!
Well! We'll be back!
[POCHI]
Ooo, an adventure!
[ZENA]
Strange.
They seem to like
working for you.
[SATOU]
Yeah, they do.
Those girls don't deserve
to live their lives as slaves.
But for now,
they're safer that way.