[WAITRESS A]
Here you are.
I'm sorry about the wait.
I hope you enjoy
your dinner, sir.
Thank you.
Here, you can keep
the change, miss.
Thanks.
[PATRON]
Hey! This isn't salty enough!
Oh, shut up!
For what you're paying,
you're lucky it has salt at all!
[PATRON]
You cheap old miser!
I hope you get stewed alive
in a witch's cauldron
and eaten for breakfast!
[BARKEEP]
How about I eat you, jerk?
[SATOU]
Everybody take a deep breath!
Relax!
The next round is on me!
[cheers]
[SATOU]
Phew. All done.
Time to hit the road.
[SATOU]
Wait a second.
Is this tavern a brothel, too?
Wee!
[MIA]
Hmm... Impure.
Awww!
You have more girls than
you know what to do with!
Yet you still go to a brothel?
[SATOU] There are so many
painfully obvious reasons
why I'm choosing not to
dignify that with a comment.
[DOSAN]
Move it!
Watch where you're
walking, peasant.
You're in my way!
[SHIMUSA]
Forgive me, sir!
[SATOU] Huh? Why is moustache
givin' me the evil eye?
Be careful.
That man.
He's mean.
Oh yeah?
[LIZA]
You know him.
He tried to take our flying ant
cores back in Seiryuu City.
[SATOU]
Right. That small time crook.
Here. Take this;
you'll feel much better.
Please.
[SHIMUSA]
Huh? A magic potion?
[FEMALE VILLAGER]
We've nothing to pay you with.
No need.
[SHIMUSA]
Oh! Thank you!
[FEMALE VILLAGER]
You're very kind!
[SATOU] Awesome.
It works on fractures, too.
Wow. Bless you!
I am in your debt, sir!
Aren't you the big hero?
I couldn't just
leave him like that.
Right. That's really
sweet and all.
Just make sure you save
some for when we need it.
Good point. Yeah.
Hmm...
Well, next up on the agenda:
Master alchemy
and learn to make potions.
[TAMA]
Is it meat?
[POCHI]
No! It's a rabbit, silly!
[ARISA]
Now you're doing alchemy?
Just how multi-talented are you?
[SATOU] First,
I'll follow the directions.
The name of the creator pops up.
Good to know.
Next time I make an item,
I'll make sure to leave
the name section blank.
I need to learn transmutation
at some point.
I guess there's no time
like the present, right?
Here goes.
Tablet.
Go!
First, I pour in the
medicine I made earlier.
Then I gradually
add some elixir.
And finally: MP.
[SATOU] Once this light
goes away, it'll be done.
[SATOU]
Now,
if I just raise my skill
to max and transmute it!
[TAMA]
You're super smart, Arisa!
[POCHI]
You're so amazing!
[SATOU]
And just like that,
I have a high-quality
HP recovery potion.
What's this?
It says here I need to store
it in a specialized vial.
If I don't, the potion
will degrade over time.
[SATOU]
Wow, look.
These vials have magic circles
drawn on them with special ink.
Huh?
It's probably past time
for a supply run.
There's a town called
Noukee in Kuhanou County.
I should go there tomorrow.
Huh?
[TAMA]
Oh wow!
[POCHI]
You're so good at that!
I guess that's good for now.
I think I might try making
a Magic Item later tonight.
Look at you making
something cool.
Magic Item, number one.
Here, try it out.
Okay!
Let me guess: When you use it
you're supposed to get magic
to flow from your right hand
to your left, yeah?
[SATOU]
Thank you for the explanation.
'Kay! Here goes!
Huh?
What's supposed to happen?
Channel your MP.
It'll flow right into
the magic circuit.
Yeah, yeah. And, then?
And nothing.
What?
It just goes around and around
till your MP is drained.
[ARISA sighs]
So anti-climactic.
[SATOU]
Fine. I'll give it a try then.
Here goes nothing.
It's an attack!
Defend the wagon cart, girls!
Uh. Don't worry, it's me!
Sorry to freak you out!
[sighs]
I've never seen this before.
There are big blank spots
all over this map.
I don't want to put
everyone in danger,
so I should probably spend
some time studying it.
Better safe than sorry.
Oh, an alchemy shop?
Yeah.
Just head straight that way till
you get to the edge of town.
[DOSAN]
Uh! Watch it!
Sorry. I didn't see you there!
[DOSAN]
Be more careful next time, kid!
Outta my way.
Time to go to the next shop.
Let's get a move on.
You stupid, worthless slave.
Yes, sir.
[DOSAN]
You're slow as molasses!
[SATOU]
Hmm...
Come on, let's go.
Oh. Right!
Afternoon, sir.
[SATOU]
Hi there.
I'm looking for some
elixir for a potion.
Do you have any?
[LENMARIS]
Hmm.
If they're
for stamina recovery,
I have three I can sell you.
They're one silver coin each.
There's a bit of a
core shortage though.
So I can't give you a discount.
[SATOU]
Core.
So that what it's made from?
If core's what I need,
I have plenty left over from
the Labyrinth and the Cradle.
Awesome.
Do you happen to
have any stabilizers?
Yeah. As a matter of fact, I do.
[SATOU] Also, if you have
any scrolls, I'll take 'em.
I need cores higher
than grade three.
Trade me and it's a done deal.
[SATOU] Wait. Isn't it
illegal to buy or sell cores?
I'll just take the potion vials.
Sorry.
I would, but someone bought up
my stock before you got here.
I tried to tell them "no," but
they had a requisition warrant
with the seal of the
viceroy of Sedum City,
so I didn't have a choice.
[SATOU]
That guy from before.
[LENMARIS]
Are you in dire need?
I'd check out the
pottery workshop.
They usually have
a decent variety.
[SATOU]
Liza.
Go on back with the others.
I'll be there soon.
[LIZA]
Is something wrong?
I need to make a quick stop.
[LIZA]
I should come with you.
[SATOU]
No, it's cool.
Get dinner ready.
I'll be with you in no time.
As you wish.
[LENMARIS] These are some
nice cores you've got here.
Go on, take any
one you'd like, sir.
[SATOU]
That all you got?
[LENMARIS]
I have more.
But I'm not too keen on selling
potentially lethal scrolls
to virtual strangers,
but how about this?
It's called "Blow."
A Magic Scroll typically
used to help stranded ships
get back to shore.
[SATOU] Who knows what's waiting
for us in those blank map areas?
[SATOU]
Shield.
Sonar.
Signal.
Blow.
[SATOU]
Hey, not bad.
I feel like a total creeper.
[gasps]
Uh-oh.
Not good.
Why do I get the feeling
something is telling me
to stay the hell out?
The Forest of Illusions?
It doesn't exactly
live up to its name.
This place is disappointing.
I guess the Forest Witch knows
I penetrated the barrier.
I should make myself scarce.
[INENIMAANA spell chant]
Toss Stone!
[gasps]
Yikes! Yikes!
Pay me no attention,
I'm just a lowly merchant
passing through!
I'll go now!
Sound good?
My magic's not working on him!
Mistress, help me!
[SATOU]
Hey, calm down.
It's okay.
Seriously, I have no
interest in hurting you.
Do you want pay back?
You can totally hit me.
I won't resist.
[SATOU]
Umm...
[WITCH]
Hmm...
Huh?
It is a true pleasure
to meet you, sir.
Welcome to the
Forest of Illusions.
I am the witch in charge of
guarding the mana source
in these woods.
[SATOU]
Umm...
[WITCH]
Forgive my apprentice.
Purity of heart and
naiveté go hand in hand.
It was foolish of Ine to attack
an emissary of Bolenan.
My apologies.
Emissary of Bolenan?
Oh, right.
She must think that because
of the bell I got from Mize.
Actually, ma'am,
I'm just a merchant.
I do have an elf from the
Bolenan Clan under my care,
but believe me: I'm no emissary.
[WITCH]
Inenimaana.
Knock before you
barge into a room.
Dear, sir.
Forgive me for earlier!
Heh. It's my fault for stumbling
into your Forest like a moron.
Please stand up;
there's no need to apologize.
Thank you for your patience
with my young apprentice, sir.
It's all right.
[WITCH]
Ine.
How are the potions
coming along?
Don't worry, Mistress!
All is well!
At this rate, I've no doubt
we'll keep our end of the deal!
Huh? What deal?
Ine is referring to a pact
we made with Count Kuhanou.
The arrangement is simple:
In return for keeping outlaws,
hunters, and other vagabonds
out of our sacred forest,
we deliver him 300 vials
of a special potion
twice a year.
Oh, I see.
Tell me, son, do you have
any interest in potions?
Yes.
But I just now started learning.
[WITCH]
In that case,
would you like me to teach
you a very special recipe?
Are you for real?
[WITCH]
Yes.
But may I ask for
one small favor in return?
[SATOU]
Of course. I'm glad to help.
Thank you for everything.
Are you sure
you don't need us
to guide you back
home, young man?
[SATOU]
Yeah, I'm fine.
All the same,
here is a small gift.
[spell chant]
Hoho.
[SATOU]
Thank you so much.
I guess I'll be on my way now.
[SATOU] She did one for me,
now I need to do one for her.
Should be fun.
Apparently, the person
I promised the witch
I'd deliver this letter
to is a giant of the forest.
Here goes.
Forest of Illusions.
I thought this place
didn't live up to its name.
I was wrong.
[ARISA grumbles]
Where in the heck
have you been all night?
You pervert!
Where you at a brothel again?
Grody.
[BIRKINZ]
Well. Any word?
Nothing yet.
Oh yeah?
Well, they're running out
of time, that's for sure.
Sundown will be here
in the blink of an eye.
Either way, it won't matter.
That's one delivery
that's never going to reach
its destination, trust me.
[OWNER]
Hey, money bags!
Aren't you the guy that
wanted to put in an order?
Yes, I am.
Thank you for seeing me, sir.
You own this place, right?
So, do we have a deal?
Can you make me
the vials or not?
I'm afraid it's a little more
complicated than that, kid.
There's a ton of regulation
here inside the city.
But there is a way.
For example, you're more than
welcome to learn pottery
at my workshop.
Wait. Is that code?
[OWNER]
An ale, please!
[WAITRESS B]
Yes, sir!
[DOSAN] When you officially
become the new viceroy in town,
the very least you can do is
make my clan your worker bees.
You're right.
Loyalty should
always be rewarded.
But I won't be viceroy.
In fact, I'm going to be
named lord of my own territory.
[SATOU]
He's just some failed noble
talking a bunch of nonsense.
[BIRKINZ] To be sure, building
a new town is no small feat.
But will I ever give up?
No.
Look who's here!
[gasps]
We came to take you back home!
Right now.
Pardon the interruption, Master,
but it is well past
your bedtime.
[laughs]
Thank you for looking
after our master, sir!
We hope to see you soon!
Yeah!
How in the heck did you find me?
Secret.
[SATOU groans]
[SATOU]
All right, time to make pottery.
Whoa. It's Ine.
Is there something wrong?
Yeah.
Looks like someone I know is
being chased by bad guys!
Huh? Well,
let's do something, then!
Come on!
[LIZA]
Right.
[POCHI]
Up and way we go!
[TAMA]
Hang on, Lulu!
[LULU]
Pochi! Tama! Put me down!
They're gonna catch me!
[SATOU]
Liza! Pochi! Tama!
Don't let the bad guys
near the carriage!
[GIRLS agree]
Are you okay?
[INENIMAANA]
Yes! Satou!
We're here to help you.
So that's what
they're after, huh?
Yeah. They want
these for the pact.
Go on.
We can handle things here, Ine!
Right.
[screams]
[crash]
[INENIMAANA gasps]
The potions!
[cries]
Don't let them get away, girls!
Go after them!
[LIZA, TAMA, POCHI agree]
[SATOU]
All right.
For now, we need
to take an inventory.
[ARISA] So out of the 300 vials
of potion you started with
only a 120 are left.
Jeez, that means a
180 were lost in the crash.
The vial on this one broke, but
there's still some left inside.
If I put these in storage...
Okay, that's enough
for about 40 vials.
Come on, let's go.
We should deliver them
what we have.
I'm sure they'll understand.
[BIRKINZ sighs]
That is too bad.
But a pact is a pact after all.
Deliver all 300 vials
of potion by sundown,
or we no longer have a deal.
[INENIMAANA]
But... But, sir!
[SATOU]
Hold on.
I've heard his voice before.
Wait...
It's creepy moustache guy.
[SATOU]
It's useless.
I can't get any info.
For now.
[ARISA]
Please, sir.
Let us explain.
[DOSAN]
Shut your mouth, peasant girl!
If we want to hear
you speak, we will say so!
Oh yeah?
[SATOU]
If you stoop to a bully's level
or let them get under your skin,
then you've already lost.
Now--
Huh?
Is there something
else you need?
[SATOU] Sadly, we lost
about a 180 vials of potion
due to the incident earlier.
You would like us to somehow
replace the missing vials
and deliver them
to you by today.
Did I get any
part of that wrong?
I just need to convince him
to give us permission
to buy the rest of the
potions from the market.
Yes, in fact you did.
First of all, this pact
is between Count Kuhanou
and the Witch of
the Forest of Illusions.
It is not your concern.
Secondly, the only potions
we will accept
are ones made by the witch.
[SATOU]
Wait just a second.
The witch said the words
"special potion."
She didn't say anything about
her being the one required
by the pact to make it.
Besides, the witch
wasn't doing the work.
Ine was the one making the
potions when I was there.
I'm not a hundred percent sure,
but I feel like maybe this guy
wants the delivery to fail
so the pact will fall apart.
Not maybe. Definitely.
[gasps]
I remember him now!
These are the two shady guys
I saw chatting at the tavern!
[BIRKINZ]
But I won't be viceroy.
In fact, I'm going to be named
lord of my own territory.
[SATOU]
So what is their plan exactly?
To break the pact and get
rid of the Forest of Illusions
so they can build a new
town right on top of it?
Whoever these guys are,
they're up to no good.
I could be wrong, but I don't
think that's part of the pact.
Unless the details
of the arrangement
have totally changed, friend.
Tell me: Why should I discuss
the details of my business
with a mere commoner like you?
Because I was a guest
of the witch recently,
and I know you're
not telling the truth.
Very well then.
I'll keep our deal
and take deliveries
provided they're the same
quality as the witch's brew.
One more thing,
what if I bring you potions that
are of a much higher quality?
Will you honor the deal then?
Heh. If you think you
can collect them all,
then be my guest.
[SATOU]
I need your assurances.
In writing, please.
What? How dare you?
Mind your tongue, you rogue!
[SATOU]
You'll have to forgive me, sir.
I'm a merchant,
which means I trust no one.
You--!
[ARISA] Who does he think
he is calling me a peasant?
[SATOU laughs]
Time to go.
[INENIMAANA] We only have three
bells left until sundown!
There is no way
this plan will work out!
Don't you worry.
My master is a cheating fraud,
but he always comes
to the rescue in the end!
[MIA]
Satou.
[LIZA]
Master. We've returned.
Right. Thanks.
[POCHI]
We brought you the plants!
[TAMA]
Lots and lots a plants!
[INENIMAANA]
Aw! You don't get it!
Even with all the
ingredients in the world,
it's still impossible!
And why is that?
Even if we do manage
to make the potions,
it won't matter if we don't
have the vials to store them in!
We'll never make
the delivery in time!
[LENMARIS]
Sorry.
I would but someone bought up
my stock before you got here.
He fell for it!
If the fool really thinks all he
has to do is make more potion,
he's in for a rude awakening!
We've been had.
What do you mean?