Thank you for this food!
[ALL]
[ARISA]
This looks so good!
Thank you for this food.
Liza, it's great.
Also, Lulu and Nana,
you worked hard, too.
It's our pleasure.
[SATOU]
Her tail's wagging.
She's really happy.
[chuckles]
Mia.
I didn't know you
were a picky eater.
No meat.
It's yuck.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot,
elves don't eat meat!
Don't worry,
I still eat meat and nothing's
gonna change that, ever!
Who doesn't like meat?
[TAMA]
It's the best ever!
It's all right, Mia,
to each her own.
[POCHI sighs]
I think maybe I ate too much!
[TAMA]
Yeah, me too!
Liza, why are you
still cooking food?
I'm pretty sure
everyone is stuffed.
Oh. I thought we might
want some provisions
for the long
journey ahead.
Awesome.
That's a smart move.
Ya know what's even smarter?
Storing it in here!
[SATOU]
What's that?
[ARISA]
An Item Box.
It's awesome.
It's like what you'd
find in a video game.
You store whatever
you want inside.
And whenever you need it,
you can pull it back out.
Just don't overdo it, though!
It'll use up all your mana!
[SATOU]
It uses MP?
That's totally different
from my storage.
[LIZA]
They're finished.
[ARISA]
Okay. Thank you so much, Liza!
[LIZA]
No, thank you.
[ARISA]
I'll take it from here!
[SATOU] Actually,
now that I think about it,
I don't really know what
my storage can do.
I should figure
that out at some point.
[SATOU]
You know.
This place isn't so bad.
Well.
When I find the time, I should
figure out my storage device.
Ladies!
Before we take off,
make sure you've taken care of
your assignments, all right?
[GIRLS agree]
Hooray!
This'll be fun!
[SATOU]
She's looking better.
After what she's been through,
that's really saying something.
It's a long journey home,
but I have a feeling
she's gonna do just fine.
And yet...
Uh...
Hey! I have an idea!
What do you think
about me touching up
the straw seat cushions
before we hit the road?
The cushions?
What's wrong, are they defective
or something like that?
Uh... Kind of.
Basically, the stupid
straws keep poking me
right in my bottom!
Gotcha.
In that case, we should
definitely fix 'em!
All right, ladies,
let's get the cloth off
these straw bundles, ASAP.
Undo this string,
and it'll come right off.
Okie-dokies!
Aye, aye!
Mia, If you see
any straws poking out
from the unwrapped bundles,
your job is to yank them out!
This should fix our problem.
If we put the leather
on the part we sit on,
the straw won't poke through.
Are you sure about this?
Goat skin is pricey!
I know.
But I don't want everyone's
butts to get all scratched up
'cause I decided
to be a cheap skate.
That's a wise choice!
If our butts get scratched,
they won't be as soft!
[SATOU]
She is the weirdest.
Whoa! He's so fast!
How is it possible for a person
to sew with such speed?
You're the fastest
of all time, Master!
The fastest of the fast!
Huh?
What the hell?
"What the hell," my ass!
Did you seriously forget to
knot the end of the thread?
My bad.
[TAMA]
Meat?
[POCHI]
Look at that birdie-bird.
It's so round and plump!
[MIA]
Cute.
Pardon me, Master!
May I please look
after this larval creature?
[chuckles]
You like it, huh?
Yes.
It's furry and round.
And it's quite cute, too.
In that case,
it's all yours, Nana.
[MIA whines]
Don't be upset,
I'll make one for you, too.
Sound good?
Lookie! It's a tiny Tama!
Yes! And here's
a petite Pochi, too!
[MIA]
Bunny.
Huh?
If I don't make one
of these for everyone,
there's gonna be
serious hell to pay.
[TAMA] Look it, I'm
touching Pochi's ears!
[POCHI]
I'm touching Tama's ears, too!
They're so fluffy!
[TAMA]
Feel how soft Pochi's ears are.
[POCHI] Yeah!
Her tail is super cute, too!
Beg your Pardon, Master.
Should we begin making
preparations to depart?
Yeah. Sounds good.
Maybe it's best to let the
horses rest a while longer.
Plus, Pochi and Tama are
having the time of their lives.
Huh. Maybe she's tired cause
she's not used to long trips?
Let's hang out here
a little bit longer, okay?
Of course, Master.
[SATOU]
What is that?
Huh.
All right, troops!
Listen up!
These are your
new marching orders!
Conduct a full and
thorough search
around that stone
outcropping over there!
'Kay!
Okie-dokie!
--Yay!
[ARISA]
That looks like fun!
I think I'd like to join them!
[SATOU] I'll call you when
it's time to leave, girls!
So don't wander off too far!
[whistling tune]
[SATOU]
You're awesome, Mia.
[MIA]
Huh?
Really?
Yeah.
[giggles]
Princess Mia.
Please instruct me on how
to make such beautiful music
with a simple leaf.
Not a princess.
Yes, you are.
Nana.
Mia doesn't like
being called Princess.
Ya mind not calling her that?
Please forgive me, Master.
I have officially
confirmed her name change
in my system's database.
[SATOU]
That was easy.
[various whistling tunes]
[whine]
Uh?
Satou?
[SATOU]
I feel so judged right now.
I know!
Behold the skill of someone
with level 10 musicianship.
[high-pitched squealing tune]
Ugh. That sounds like the
noise a dying mouse makes
when it gets its head
snapped in a mousetrap.
[MIA]
No more.
[LULU]
Oh! Don't worry, Master,
if you keep practicing
your instrument,
you'll get better
one of these days!
If you try hard,
you can do anything!
Uh. Thank you.
Stop goofing off and
come with me right now!
Look there.
Oh, what?
[SATOU]
Whoa.
Stone torii?
At first glance,
I couldn't make it out.
But from what I can see,
it seems like three
torii in a row fell over.
There must have
been a shrine here.
[SATOU]
It's weird, but...
...I feel like I've
seen this place before.
But how?
[GIRL]
Ichiro.
Never forget this.
We will be together
until the end of time.
You will always be Ichiro,
no matter the world or era
in which you find yourself.
So is reincarnation real?
[GIRL]
It is... but...
...reincarnation isn't enough.
[SATOU]
I remember.
That shrine in the background
is the one that was near
my grandpa's place.
But who's the girl
with the weird hair?
Is she my friend from
when I was little?
[GIRL] The lifespan of a human
is different than that of a God.
In order for us
to stay together,
we need divine intervention.
[SATOU] The Kagura:
a dance dedicated to a god
who fell in love
with a human being.
[GIRL]
Ichiro.
You can.
[ARISA]
Master!
Snap out of it, will ya?
Uh. What's wrong?
[sighs] A cliff isn't exactly
the perfect location
for a daydream, ya dum-dum!
[SATOU]
What just happened?
I wasn't the victim of
a psychological attack.
And the torii at the shrine near
my grandpa's place were red.
Plus, none of my firends
looked anything like that girl.
Wait a sec!
When I was a student,
I made a doujin game with a
shrine almost exactly like that!
I don't remember having that
conversation in real life.
It must be a part
of the game I made.
What's your deal?
You're spacing out again!
[SATOU]
Uh, I'm sorry.
I was just thinking
about the shrine
where I used to
play when I was a kid.
Huh?
[SATOU]
Whoa.
This looks like a
broken Travel Gate.
Wait, a Travel Gate?
You mean like the warp
feature that shows up
in some video games?
Can you fix it?
Probably not.
Quick.
Let's go find Pochi and Tama.
It's time to ship out.
Lookie, Master,
I found us some prey!
Master, since we were able
to procure some meat,
I have one small request before
we continue the journey ahead.
May I butcher that?
[SATOU]
Sure. Why not?
[LULU]
Liza.
If you're willing, I'd be very
interested to learn your skill.
[LIZA]
Come.
I will teach you
the art of butchering.
You can take it apart, Lulu.
[LULU]
Fun!
[SATOU] Oh, no, her hair's
filled with sand.
Hey, Mia.
Do you know of
a Water Magic spell
that's kinda like the
Everyday Magic Soft Wash?
No.
I see.
[TAMA]
Look here!
I brought us some meat!
Awesome, Tama, great job!
Wow! Now that's adorable!
[SATOU]
A baby monster.
[ARISA]
Oh, can I hold it, please?
Yeah, sure!
[SATOU] It may be cute,
but it's a baby monster,
so be careful, all right?
Yeah, yeah.
[ARISA shrieks]
[TAMA]
Come back!
The prey ran away from me.
No, Tama, it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
It squirmed
right out of my arms.
[TAMA]
No.
I'm sorry I messed up, Master.
I tried, but I couldn't
catch the prey.
[SATOU]
It's fine.
You're safe;
that's what matters now.
Besides, there's
always next time.
Right?
[TAMA]
Right!
Next time I'm gonna catch
the biggest, baddest beast
in the whole world!
All this excitement has
made me hungry for a snack.
I've got a great idea:
We should eat the
pancakes from before!
This thing's pretty convenient.
But it doesn't exactly
keep your food warm.
Sorry girls, they probably
don't taste very good cold.
Tastes pretty darn good to me!
Yeah, it's yummy!
[SATOU] Now, let's see
what we have here.
A spell book on shadow magic?
What the--?
Oh, right!
Zen's mementos
are now in my inventory.
This could be good.
Maybe I can learn
more about magic.
All right.
I've finished my lesson
on Shadow Magic.
Wow.
It's really amazing how
compatible the magic
in this world is to
programming language.
It's almost as if the person
who created the magic in
this place is a programmer.
Now to the task at hand:
I wanna get a handle
on this whole
Water-Magic-Washing-Spell thing
so Pochi can get cleaned up.
I'll look into
Everyday Magic next.
[SATOU groans]
Everyday Magic is
a huge pain in the ass.
I can't seem to wrap
my head around it.
My Water Magic idea is a no go.
But wait,
just like Mia tried to copy
Arisa's humming by ear.
If I consider the techniques
needed for Everyday Magic,
copy and paste the existing
parts of Water Magic
into the formula,
I should be able
to make a new spell.
I love getting my hands
on this kind of research.
I could do it for hours.
Uh... Wait a second.
Huh?
[ARISA]
Master, stop it!
You've had enough for one night!
[MIA]
Bad boy.
[SATOU]
That was totally not my fault.
Satou.
It's uncouth to be a perv.
That was naughty.
Everyone knows
you're not allowed
to squeeze a woman's bits
till after you're wed.
It's true.
To squeeze, get on your knees.
You had me worried for a second
because your eyes
were wide open,
but you weren't
responding at all!
[SATOU]
I don't wanna freak them out.
I need to make sure
my eyes are closed
when I'm looking at the menu.
Relax, I'm fine.
I was just concentrating
on learning a new
spell, that's all.
Learning a new spell?
Since when are you a bona fide
researcher of magic spells?
I'm not.
I just built one and
was tinkering with it is all.
If it's all right, Mia, I'd like
you to help me with it later.
Mm. 'Kay.
[SATOU]
Huh?
Whoa! These pop-ups.
Ratmen?
Thank you for
all your help, Satou.
So what's up next for you?
A good question.
I must go find my friends.
Sadly, we were all separated
while trying to
save the princess.
[SATOU]
Liza!
Stop the carriage!
Zeze. Jene. Mitoro. Hoze. Rada!
[MALE RATMAN A]
Brincess, you're safe!
[FEMALE RATMAN]
Oh, Brincess!
Mia's protectors?
[SATOU]
They acted as decoys,
so she could safely
escape the Cradle.
Girls.
I think we should
make camp here tonight.
[MIA]
Satou.
[SATOU]
What's up?
You all right?
[MIA]
You two. Talk.
Okay.
My brave, sir, thank you
so much for saving us.
That said, we have
something important
which requires our attention.
We must leave at once.
Oh. Of course.
Go on ahead, we'll catch up
with you guys tomorrow.
Ahhh!
[POCHI]
Oh! That was awesome!
Meat's back on the menu!
That was expertly done, Tama!
Thanks!
Well, shall I cook
the meat, then, Master?
That sounds great.
Let me know if
you need help, okay?
I must say, Tama,
I'm quite impressed with you.
You are truly
a genius hunter, Tama.
[chuckles]
Not bad, kiddo.
Check me out, Tama, do you like
my crazy awesome meat dance?
You know I do, Pochi!
Huh...
Hey, Mia.
Ya wanna help me with that
spell I told you about before?
[MIA]
Mm-hmm.
[spell chant]
Bubble Bath Time.
Look at us!
We're so clean!
We sparkle!
Great success.
Thanks a lot, Mia.
[SATOU]
This sucks.
I'm bored out of my mind.
I could make another new spell.
No. I'm supposed to
be on the night watch.
Wait!
How about I try my
little storage experiment?
[SATOU] I can store
things from far away.
Cool.
[SATOU]
Not that far.
Oh, well.
At least now I know--
the threshold for this
is about three meters.
[SATOU]
Ohh...
I can separate each
component of blended things.
In that case,
I can make salt water drinkable.
That'll come in handy!
Especially near the ocean!
Aww man, it doesn't
work with salt water.
Too bad.
Wait.
I bet I can dissect those
insect corpses I got back
at the Cradle.
If I can swing that, Liza won't
have to take apart the prey
Pochi and Tama bring
back to the camp for us.
[SATOU]
No dice.
Man, this isn't going very well.
[SATOU]
But...
...I didn't lose any MP.
I guess mine is different
from Arisa's Item Box.
I should check out hers, too.
[yawns]
Yeah, it's official.
Her storage is definitely weak
sauce compared to my apparatus.
It's useless.
Wait.
Hold on.
The flame went out.
Apparently, the stuff in the
Item Box changes over time.
On the other hand,
my storage is different.
The status of the items
in my storage apparatus
doesn't change at all.
Who knows?
Maybe time stops in there?
Or maybe it's like a game,
and it's just a bunch
of data stored inside.
I think I have a brilliant idea.
It's so warm!
And it's yummy, too!
Yum in my tum!
I didn't know
you were planning
to reheat the stew
from yesterday, Master!
Thank you, that was
incredibly thoughtful!
Ah, It was nothing.
So what do you think?
How does it taste?
Not bad.
Ah. Sparkly sparks!
[SATOU]
We've got company.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[SATOU]
Oh wow.
This is a grave for all the
ratmen who died protecting Mia.
[MIZE]
Mr. Satou.
I thank you for rescuing
all my friends.
I am in your debt.
My pleasure.
My friends.
Thank you.
[MIA] I, Misanaria of the
Bolenan Forest, ask you,
most Sacred and Ancient Trees.
Please let the brave ratmen
who perished valiantly
rest in peace from this day
until the end of time.
[MIZE] I wish to
bestow you with this bell.
It was hand crafted
by the elves.
As you have garnered the
trust of Princess Misanaria.
I shall trust you in return.