Did this sword commit murder?
What?
[MARO] If asking if the sword
magically walked in here
of its own volition and
killed the imperial envoy.
When searching for one
single grain of sand,
a wise man will choose
to run the entire beach
through a sieve. Understand?
[MASAMUNE] You sure know how
to attract attention, Kiku.
Let's go...
they'll be coming soon.
I know it's
a lot to ask,
but do you think it would be
alright if I came with you?
I suppose
you'll have to.
[KIKUCHIYO] But he'll
change his mind soon enough.
I'll bring up the rear!
[GOROBEI]
Forget them! Come on!
Kikuchiyo!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
You better not screw this up!
Save those farmers, okay!
♪ opening song ♪
[YOHEI] What is a
Nobuseri doing here?
They're attacking!
I think they were just
checkin' on the harvest.
The rice is
about to bend.
And still no samurai yet.
They're gone.
Anyone got any
brilliant plans?
We could fight
our way out, sensei.
But we can't wage war
on empty stomachs can we?
We were in such a hurry
when we fled the city...
I left the rice behind...
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's not
what I meant...
It's time we call on old allies,
and lay low for a while.
[GOROBEI] Got someone
special in mind?
The only one I'd trust
is my former mate.
You mean you
were married Sensei?
Of course I'm not sure
if that's still an option.
We'll leave here at sunset...
Everyone rest up until then.
[PROSTITUTE] Wanna have
some fun tonight, big man?
[MISTER]
Maybe next time, honey.
[FIREFLY CHORUS]
♪ Leave grief at the door, ♪
♪ Sit back and let us pour... ♪
♪ Have a drink then
have one more, ♪
♪ 'Cause that's
what sake's for... ♪
♪ Too much pain in life, ♪
♪ So lose the
sword and knife... ♪
♪ Dance your stress away, ♪
♪ If only for today... ♪
♪ Forget your cares,
forget your strife, ♪
♪ An' tonight
forget your wife... ♪
♪ Eat it up... ♪
♪ Drink it down... ♪
♪ At Firefly House! ♪
[CHEERING]
[MERCHANT]
All right, now it's my turn!
[SHAMISEN MUSIC]
[FIREFLY CHORUS]
♪ Leave grief at the door, ♪
♪ Sit back and let us pour... ♪
♪ Have a drink then
have one more, ♪
♪ 'Cause that's
what sake's for... ♪
♪ Too much pain in life... ♪
[RONIN SAMURAI]
Lousy merchants...
How 'bout a refill?
[OLD LADY]
How 'bout you pay first?
No money, no sake.
[FIREFLY CHORUS]
♪ So eat it up... ♪
♪ Drink it down... ♪
♪ At the Firefly House! ♪
[CHEERING IN BACKGROUND]
[RONIN SAMURAI
GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[SHICHIROJI]
Whoa there...
Please, allow me to
carry this for you.
Thanks, Shichiroji,
you're too kind.
Oh please,
it's nothin'.
Ah... That hits the spot!
[YUKINO] Honey?
Oh, Yukino!
I thought you were
on call tonight.
[YUKINO]
Drinking leftovers again?
You know you can have your own.
Y'know,
old habits and all--
I hate to see
things go to waste.
Mmm... That is good...! Anago ?
[YUKINO] Yes, we got
some nice conger eels
from the Seiso Trench.
Mm-Mmm! I've died
and gone to heaven.
The fireflies are dancing
all around you tonight...
They like you.
[CRASHING SOUND]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Please don't
do anything rash.
Come on... It's me.
[YUKINO SIGHS]
[MERCHANT]
If it's money you want,
I've got more than
I know what to do with!
I don't want your filthy coins!
Ahh...!
Great Samurai, please
put away your sword--
we can talk
this through.
You're not fit to
address me, wench!
When Lord Shingen invaded
the fortress of Rock-Face,
I distinguished myself
as his third spear man!
That was before
you merchants came...
reducing heroes to beggars!
Ahh! Huh...?!
Now, now, you won't
be needing this in here.
If you don't get outta
my way I'll cut you down!
[SHICHIROJI]
Tempting offer. But no thanks.
[RONIN SAMURAI GRUNTS]
[RONIN SAMURAI YELLS]
You'll pay for that!
This town's a sanctuary...
The Village of Respite...
You should raise your cup,
not your sword...
So how about it?
My treat of course.
You have no idea what
it means to be a samurai.
You know the whole Samurai thing
went out of style years ago--
why don't you give it a rest?
I think you'd be a great dancer.
A samurai is
never anything else!
[RONIN SAMURAI YELLS]
[SHICHIROJI]
Thanks for coming,
and do watch your
step on the way out!
Uh... Ah... Ah...
[RONIN SAMURAI YELLS]
[CROWD LAUGHS]
You've... shamed me...
[SHICHIROJI]
Haven't you heard?
They're hunting samurai.
You're gonna have
trouble fitting in
here or in Kougakyo...
...unless you're ready to
renounce your warrior ways.
You'll regret this!
Aww! Hey wait!
The bill...! Ah!
[SHICHIROJI YELLS]
[KIRARA]
It's so beautiful.
But what does everybody
do down there?
Well they... uhm...
They purge all the pent-up
stress from their bodies
and cleanse their minds of
life's trials and tribulations.
[KATSUSHIRO] So it's like
a wash-house for the soul?
I didn't know they had those.
Your social status doesn't
mean anything past those walls.
And neither does
the magistrate's power--
it's a little pocket of freedom.
Well that's what
they say, anyway.
Now, what about
Kikuchiyo-dono?
[KATSUSHIRO] You've been
thinking about him, too?
Relax--not even hell would be
dumb enough to take him in.
I doubt we've seen
the last of him.
[WHISTLING SOUND]
[KIKUCHIYO] Okay, I'm getting
really tired of this, guys.
But if you don't want
your lives, I'll take 'em!
Aw, c'mon...!
This only works if you come
running at me, you stupid goats!
[YUKINO]
Hm...
I thought you weren't
going to do anything rash.
Yeah, that's the
problem with pride...
[YUKINO]
You or that drunk samurai?
These days, a samurai's
only options are either
find work as a bodyguard or
join up with the Nobuseri.
You're neither of those
things and you're a samurai.
I gave that up.
You're a terrible liar,
I know what makes you happy.
You know how when fireflies
are just young little glowworms,
they flit about in the water,
stirring up bubbles
and making noise?
Yes, feasting on snails
and slugs and other things.
Yet when they're grown they
settle, and become silent.
My splashing days are over.
I'll be right here for
the rest of my life...
Because I owe this life to you.
Knock it off...
Or I might believe you.
Is something wrong?
It's good to find you alive...
Shichiroji-san.
As I live and breathe...
[KAMBEI]
We need shelter for the night.
Well of course you do!
[KAMBEI]
Sorry for the imposition...
C'mon!
[KIRARA]
We thank you.
[WHISTLING SOUND]
[KOMACHI]
Oh, I don't like that noise.
[WHISTLING SOUND]
A sea imp?
Ahh!
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm no imp! I'm a samurai!
[KYUZO]
Don't help.
A machine samurai
has been spotted,
in the Village of Respite.
[UKYO]
Mm-Hmm...
Then what are we waiting for?
I'd like you all to meet
my old mate, Shichiroji.
Lady Shichiroji...
[KAMBEI COUGHS]
Katsushiro, this guy.
Ah... Oh...
Mm-Hmm...
You goof...
You thought he meant
"mate" in the literal sense?
[KAMBEI]
Heh, heh, heh...
He and I shared the thrills and
sorrows of war for many years.
Oh, I get it.
So the young
lady is...?
[YUKINO]
I'm Yukino.
Shichiroji-dono,
you lucky dog...
to have such
a beautiful wife!
Oh no, not quite...
Roji and I aren't married.
I'd love to hear the
story of how you two met.
[YUKINO]
Oh, it was nothing.
I just... fished him
out of the river.
So he used
to be a fish?
It'll have been...
five years soon.
Hey! Just like Momotaro
in that old fairy tale.
I guess you're right...
The little baby
inside of a peach,
floating down the river...
[LAUGHING]
So you've got
Ayamaro after you.
Yeah, for some reason that
guy's really got it in for us.
I heard that an
envoy was murdered.
Convenient excuse
for a samurai hunt.
They've been
looking for one.
Suppose the Magistrate's
men were to come here,
to Firefly House--how long
could we hold them off?
Not long if even at all...
But there is a
secret escape route.
Will it take us outside
of Kougakyo's boundaries?
If you can make it past
the lair of the
Shikimoribito--the Guardians.
Why, has that been a problem
for people in the past?
Not sure... No one's ever
made it back to let me know.
That's enough scary
talk for one evening.
I want you all to
have a full taste of
the Firefly House experience.
[HEIHACHI]
Now this is what I call luxury!
Oh, man...!
The rice is great!
It's from Omachi?
Yes, how
can you tell?
I'm better with a
pair of chopsticks
than I am with a sword.
Would you mind
passing this around?
Are you all right Katsushiro,
your face is turning red.
Oh it is?
I guess it's just
a little bit warm in here...
[YUKINO]
Really? Have some air.
[KOMACHI]
I think he's allergic to girls.
[GROUP LAUGHS]
You all seem like
one big happy family.
Those three over there
came to the city looking to
recruit samurai to protect
their village from the Bandits,
and one by one
we came together.
They won us over
with their pure spirit.
So a few leftovers are gonna
wage war on the Nobuseri, huh?
If that's what it
takes, then yes.
[MURMURING]
War with the Nobuseri--
but that sounds... dangerous.
Aren't you gonna eat anything
sis--it's really good!
[KIRARA] It wouldn't be right
to feast like an empress,
while the rest of
the village is starving.
Ah... don't be so hard
on yourself, you've earned this!
Back in the village we
usually don't even have
a whole fish to share between
us but maybe once a year.
[RIKICHI SIGHS]
Everyone's life is
full of suffering,
but going hungry
won't make it better...
Bodies don't last long
on a diet of virtue alone.
Please forgive my rudeness.
Uh, Honey...
Uh, how 'bout some
music to help us digest?
[SHAMISEN MUSIC]
[HEIHACHI]
Wow! I love this place!
[GOROBEI]
Heh... Apparently so.
Here, let me pour you some sake?
I don't feel
like drinking.
I know you're worried about
the rest of your village.
[KIRARA SIGHS]
[OLD LADY YAWNS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey, as long as you're bored,
why don't you take
a look at my family tree? Heh...
Now then...
which one am I again?
Huh? Don't ask me.
[KNOCKING]
[TESSAI]
Open up!
[HORN HONKS]
[ROBOTIC VOICE]
Curfew has passed,
and the Village of
Respite is closed.
Please come back
in the morning.
After closing, not even the
lord of the manor may enter.
[UKYO] Well, diplomacy won't
work. Let's find another way.
[ROBOTIC VOICE]
No exceptions will be made...
[DISTORTED ROBOTIC VOICE]
No... ex... cep... tions...
[SHICHIROJI]
I'm surprised you knew...
That I was
still alive, I mean.
You've given up
the samurai life.
Yeah... Back in that moat,
I recalled my first life...
that of a
humble vendor...
Then the dark
of night fell...
And the second
ship burned down...
As it came crashing
down around my body,
I truly thought
it would be my end.
Have you grown tired of battle?
"Battle"?
Now there's a
nostalgic word for us.
[KAMBEI] Times have certainly
changed, haven't they?
It used to be that
one would train hard
in order to go off to war,
to achieve glory, to eventually
become daimyo of his own land...
That is all any of
us ever dreamed of.
[SHICHIROJI]
Nowadays, those dreams can't be
won by sword or spear...
they're won by
the highest bid.
[KAMBEI]
Exactly.
[SHAMISEN MUSIC]
♪ I once cut down bandits
from all three thousand lands. ♪
♪ Cut them down
and got cut down. ♪
♪ But still...
But still I stand. ♪
I'll be at
your side.
There's no reward or fame.
Only a bloody war.
Are you sure?
Yes.
This time we may
meet our deaths.
[KIKUCHIYO SNORES]
[YUKINO]
Ah, to be young again.
You have such beautiful skin.
Too bad... it's always
covered with dirt and sweat.
[YUKINO]
Not tonight...
After we finish bathing,
I'll do your makeup.
[KIRARA] Oh no, I'm sorry,
I can't wear makeup.
[YUKINO]
You're so guarded...
This is where you come
to forget earthly concerns.
So that young samurai...
[KIRARA]
You mean Katsushiro?
[YUKINO]
He is awfully cute...
[KIRARA]
I really hadn't noticed.
[YUKINO]
I can tell he fancies you.
[KIRARA] I'm just not
interested in men right now.
But seeing the way that you
and Shichiroji are together
kind of gives me
hope for the future.
Oh, thank you.
But in the fairy-tale...
Momotaro always leaves
to slay the demons.
[CLATTERING SOUND]
[YUKINO GASPS]
They found you.
[KIRARA GASPS]
You're sure this is where
that machine samurai went?
[WITNESS YELLS]
You think my Kirara
is in there with him?
[YUKINO]
The hunters are outside!
[GOROBEI]
You're kidding me!
How'd they know
where we are?
I'm sure no one
saw us get here...
[KAMBEI] That's
the way war goes.
Get everybody else up!
[SHICHIROJI]
Under these floorboards,
there's a canal that'll
get us out of here.
We can take my boat.
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Hey, get your hands off of me!
[GUARD 2] We're samurai hunters.
Please come quietly.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, it's you guys. Hey!
Wanna check out my family tree?
Ah! Kiku?!
[HEIHACHI] That moron
led 'em right to us!
[GOROBEI] I swear,
he's a curse on us all!
[HEIHACHI]
D'oh! Here he comes!
[THUD]
[KAMBEI]
You're late.
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey, I've been
looking all over for you guys!
Why are you all frowning?
Well, whatever it is, rest
assured, now that I'm back,
everything will be all right!
Everything will be all right!
[UKYO] Kirara!
Oh, I've found you!
Delicate flowers don't
belong in a place like this...
Let me take you away from here.
[KIKUCHIYO] All right,
you asked for it!
I'm gonna smash you flat!
[SHICHIROJI] Hold on, this
is the Village of Respite,
where the use of
swords is forbidden.
I can't have you
breaking the rules...
[HYOGO] Shall I break
your kneecaps instead?
[GOROBEI] Didn't you hear the
man? This is a sword-free zone!
[HYOGO]
Enough excuses!
Secret Technique:
Floor Mat Fortress!
All right now follow
me down below...
Feels like old times
already, huh Kambei-sama?
[TESSAI] When I give the
signal, we all attack at once!
[UKYO]
I can't let you do that!
What if one of
these clumsy brutes
gets a scratch on my
Kirara's perfect face?!
Please...
Have some faith in our
skills Young Master.
Why should I?
Honestly Tessai, sometimes
I don't know where your head is.
[TESSAI YELLS]
Ah! Tessai,
what have you done?!
[YUKINO]
So you're really leaving.
[SHICHIROJI]
I'm sorry.
I knew you weren't through
being a samurai yet.
I hope this doesn't hurt
Firefly House too badly.
Don't worry, I can
handle a little trouble.
[KIKUCHIYO] I hate to break up
this gut wrenching farewell,
but the bad guys are comin'.
So if you're with us, let's go!
[KOMACHI]
Knock it off, Kiku!
Don't forget this.
Thanks.
I hope... I hope the
Nobuseri get you...
[KIRARA]
Lady Yukino!
Remember--Momotaro always
comes back in the end,
with a mountain of
treasure! No matter what.
[KIKUCHIYO] So wait,
this guy's name is Momotaro?
[KAMBEI] I'm sorry
I had to involve you.
[KIRARA] And it's
all because of us...
It was a nice dream
I was having,
but we all have to
wake up some time.
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
We've got company.
[KOMACHI]
Someone's up ahead, too.
Shikimoribito.
Ah...!
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI] Dear Okara.
Today was a very good day!
Even though everybody else said
that Kiku was gone for good,
I just knew he'd be back...
And he's better and stronger
and funnier than before!
As if that weren't enough
excitement for one day,
we met a new samurai.
Well, Shichiroji's not
really a samurai, anymore.
He works at a teahouse
in the Village of Respite,
which is where they wash souls.
His girlfriend, Yukino,
is so pretty and nice.
I wanna be just like her!
It's funny, most of our samurai
aren't samurai anymore.
When we found him,
Heihachi was a wood-chopper
and Gorobei is a
street performer.
I guess since the war ended,
they had to find other jobs.
If I had to get a job, I think
I'd like to be an empress.
Or maybe a pirate!
I don't know why Kambei
never took another job,
but then again,
I can't imagine him
being anything but a
samurai... or a teacher.
Oh, and I almost forgot,
I learned some new
songs at the teahouse.
I can't wait to
sing them for you!
But I'm getting
kinda sleepy now.
So bye bye...