[RIKICHI] Now, then...
Can you help us?
Hold your tongue, farmer.
Let me finish my meal first.
Oh, sure...
Well, I guess the
Elder would be happy...
We've definitely found
the hungry samurai.
I should beat you
for this mockery!
I have higher
goals than peasants!
You really think
I'd work for food?!
Poor as I am, I'm no beggar!
[UKYO]
That one... She's rare...
[TESSAI]
That is a farm girl, master...
She is a jewel
lost in the dirt...
She will sparkle brightly
once she's polished.
Young master...
[KAMBEI]
Defeat the No-Buseri?
As farmers, this is the only
payment we can give you. Rice.
As much as you can eat,
for as long as you stay.
Kirara.
Really...? Well...!
That's why they bloomed--
your name's so sweet.
She really jumped!
[GIRL SCREAMS]
That why I jumped, because
I knew you would save me.
I know that you're the one.
♪ opening song ♪
[KOMACHI GASPS]
Sister!
[RIKICHI]
Water Priestess!
Aww... Did I make
you worry, Komachi?
I'm sorry.
[RIKICHI]
Great Samurai!
[KIRARA] Great Kambei
is the one who saved me.
Do you know what happened...
to Katsushiro, then?
No, Not really...
[KAMBEI] This will be a
good chance for him to...
...reevaluate himself.
Reevaluate himself...?
What's that?
[EXPLOSION]
[POLKA DOTS YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
That hurt.
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Still breathin'?
Good. Come on, then.
Let's get moving.
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS IN PAIN]
[KATSUSHIRO]
What's wrong?
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS IN PAIN]
[KIKUCHIYO]
Piece of junk!
Kikuchiyo-dono,
are you okay?
[KIKUCHIYO]
What's it look like, kid?
[MASAMUNE]
Yeah, just like I thought...
I figured this was why
you were taking so long.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Masamune, old man!
This stupid thing's
breaking down on me again.
[MASAMUNE] Heh... That
stupid thing's your body,
you should treat it
with more care.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Who are you?
Do me a favor, Sonny,
grab that arm that's
hanging behind you there.
[AYAMARO]
I heard what happened, son...
Now tell me why
you are so afraid.
[UKYO]
Samurai came...
Samurai came and tried to
kill me, father... Kill me!
It is impossible
for anyone to kill you.
You are the one who will
inherit the fortune of Ayamaro.
You will be
Kougakyo's Magistrate...
And you are my son...
No one will ever be able to
harm you, not even the samurai.
He took her...
Things were so perfect
before he came in...
[AYAMARO]
If he bothers you so much,
why not just get rid of him?
[UKYO]
You're right.
[GUNSHOT]
If you want something done,
you have to do it yourself.
So what...
you'll kill them?
Only the machine...
I hate all machine samurai.
[TESSAI] What should
we do about the girl?
Ah, yes. Bring her to me,
I want her even more
than I did before.
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey! Kid!
Quit brooding over the fight.
You're making me twitch.
Let him brood,
you gear-head.
I don't know what
happened back there,
but he needs
to let it sink in.
[GOROBEI]
Hey there! You boy!
[KATSUSHIRO] Huh...?
[GOROBEI] That's right,
I'm talking to you.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Who's this guy?
Why are
you asking me?
I've never seen him
before in my life.
[GOROBEI]
What's the matter, boy?
You look gloomy...
Come on. You can tell me.
Oh ho. Hold on, there.
You'll have to excuse
my rudeness, young man...
A crude way of getting
your attention, I know.
It comes from being in
show business for so long...
Forgive me.
[GOROBEI LAUGHS]
Who are you?
What do you want with me?
[GOROBEI]
Pardon me!
I didn't introduce myself.
I'm Katayama Gorobei.
Entertainer second,
gentleman first.
Pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
The pleasure
is all yours...
What do you want
from me, Katayama?
[GOROBEI]
Just a little bit of fun.
I may not look it now,
but I used to be a samurai...
Unfortunately, in the current
world climate my sword is good
only for performance...
I show off my war
skills to city crowds
to scrape in my daily wage.
You use Bushido
for entertainment?!
[KIKUCHIYO] Hey!
What kind of performances?
[KATSUSHIRO]
Don't encourage him!
Why are you
so angry...?
You're still moping about
what happened back there,
aren't you, boy?
Well, that's
no good...
You're way too serious--
Just try to have some fun.
Maybe then you
won't keep snapping
at everyone who
cracks a smile...
[KATSUSHIRO]
I'm not moping!
Then why are clutching
on to that trinket
like your life
depends on it?
[GONGING]
You're absolutely
right old man,
and that's just what
I was going to tell
our young
friend, here...
You're far
too serious...
but there's nothing like
a friendly bet to fix that.
A bet?
[GOROBEI]
That's right.
Tell me, do you have
experience handling a bow?
[KATSUSHIRO]
Of course.
Then it's easy...
All you have to do is take
an arrow and aim it here.
Ah.
Oh!
[KIKUCHIYO]
This oughtta be good.
[GOROBEI]
Using only my hand,
I'll snatch the arrow you
shoot at me out of the air...
Life or death, that's the game.
If I fail, I die--
assuming your aim is good--
and you get back
at me for poking fun.
If I succeed, you have to pay
the value of any man's life--
you buy me lunch.
The rules are
as simple as that.
Here.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Alright.
Interesting man.
I wonder if he was ever really
a samurai like he claims.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Heh, ha, ha!
Well he's certainly
not anymore.
You're the expert.
Ladies and gentlemen,
lend me your eyes
for a fascinating
game of chance!
A samurai's life
is on the line!
[GIRL IN CROWD]
Oh, wow!
[MAN IN CROWD]
This guy for real?
Alright, boy, it's up
to you to make this fun.
You know your target.
Here you go...
Does this help?
This is stupid...
A samurai should
not put his life
on the line for entertainment.
It's dishonorable.
What's the matter, boy?
You nervous?
Shut up! Don't mock me!
Fine... Why don't I move
closer, make it easier...
You can aim, right?
[GOROBEI] Do it!
[CROWD YELLS IN AMAZEMENT]
[KIKUCHIYO]
He actually did it.
He's good.
[GOROBEI MOANS]
[KIKUCHIYO]
He's nuts.
Haven't I always said
samurai are strange?
[AYAMARO]
You showed good sense
bringing Ukyo here
before he was hurt.
I hate to think of the fortune
I invested in raising him
going to waste
if he were killed.
[TESSAI] Yes.
This is a
merchant city.
The new class of rulers
cannot let these warrior relics
destroy it
with swords.
This machine samurai...
Tell me, is it the
same as the No-Buseri?
[TESSAI] No. It's a type
I've never seen before...
A non-standard
model, I believe.
[AYAMARO] Hmm. I heard he was
working with someone else.
[TESSAI]
A young man.
[AYAMARO] Kill him, too.
And the peasants.
[TESSAI] The young master would
like to keep the girl, sir.
[AYAMARO] The young master
needs to learn his place.
[TESSAI]
Of course.
[KOMACHI GASPS]
Oh! Katsushiro!
I'm so glad you're safe...
Great Samurai!
[KIKUCHIYO] What?! You don't
mean that old man, do you?
Hey! Show off!
What are you doing here?
[KAMBEI]
You got your head back on.
[KIKUCHIYO DISTORTED]
The Bandits are mine--
mine-- mine to defeat...!
Find your own cause!
May you never lose that
fighting spirit of yours.
[KIKUCHIYO DISTORTED]
What's that supposed to mean?!
Get back here...! Hey!
If it's true what
they just told me...
that you saved
Lady Kirara,
then I owe you
my humble thanks.
[KAMBEI] I hear your first
battle was... difficult.
Thank you so much,
Katsushiro.
[KATSUSHIRO]
Please. Forgive me!
Forgive you for what?
[KATSUSHIRO] For failing in
my duty to protect you...
I told you not to
let go of my hand...
but I let go of yours...
It was Kikuchiyo who defeated
those guardsmen, not I...
I was disarmed soon
after the fight broke out...
It's shameful.
I call myself a samurai,
but I'm useless... useless.
At least you tried,
Katsushiro.
Everyone's all right in
the end so it doesn't matter.
Kambei-dono
spoke the truth...
If I can't even protect
one person now...
how can I hope to save a whole
village from the Bandits?
[KIRARA SCREAMS]
[KIKUCHIYO] So you've been
listening to him, huh?
[KOMACHI] Kiku! Did you
have to break the wall?
Easy, old buddy.
[KIKUCHIYO] I have to
give this samurai bastard
a piece of my mind...
You hearing me?!
Look at this.
This is your meal...
Any idea how much they sacrifice
to make sure you have it...?!
Of course you don't...!
You're a samurai after all...
They feed you all
the rice you can eat,
so you'll stay, and
meanwhile they eat millet!
Pig's food!
Go to their village.
You saved the girl so you
must be worth something.
Or is that what you
call a losing battle?!
They suffer for you and
you still won't help?!
I'll kill you right here!
[KIKUCHIYO YELLS]
[KIKUCHIYO GRUNTS]
Hey! Let go!
Did it ever occur to you
to wait for an answer?
[KIKUCHIYO]
What are you talking about?
I have decided to go with
the farmers to their village.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh. Well. That's good. Heh...
Your determination
and loyalty
have won me over
to your cause...
I will help you.
I shall not let your
treasured rice go to waste.
[RIKICHI] Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Well look at that, they finally
got themselves a samurai.
How's that feel?
[KIKUCHIYO] Feels like I
could beat Kambei now.
[KIKUCHIYO LAUGHS]
[MASAMUNE] You can give up that
dream. You'll never beat him.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Aw! Screw you!
[KAMBEI] There is nothing to
block the enemy from the air.
The bluffs will be
difficult to protect.
Sensei, perhaps we could find
a way to obtain some weapons,
then teach the farmers
themselves how to fight.
This is
a war, boy...
It's not
just a game...
And it is much
more daunting
to defend
than attack.
Yes... Sensei.
Cut that out... Why do you
keep calling me Sensei?
You're not my student.
[KATSUSHIRO]
I may not be your student...
but you are
still my teacher.
[KIKUCHIYO]
That's right! Keep sucking up!
I'm not sucking up, I'm giving
him the respect he deserves!
[KAMBEI] Stop it.
[KOMACHI]
Yeah. That's right, Stop.
[KIRARA]
Komachi...
[KOMACHI] If Katsushiro and Kiku
are both coming to help us,
they can't keep
fighting like this.
They have to start
trying to get along.
[KAMBEI] No. We will not be
taking these two with us.
But, Sensei!
[KIKUCHIYO]
What did you just say?!
I need real samurai.
[KIKUCHIYO]
I'm going to sleep!
You said there
are about 40 units
in the Bandit's
main force.
Yes, that sounds
about right.
Both Beni-gumo
and Raiden models...
We badly need to
strengthen our forces...
Only experienced warriors will
be able to stand up to them...
I'll need seven samurai,
including myself.
[KIRARA]
Seven...
But the Elder only gave
us permission for four.
Are you sure
Kiku won't do?
[RIKICHI] The Great Samurai
has told us his decision.
We will trust in Kambei's
wisdom no matter what, sister.
Then it's decided. We should
start searching the city now.
Six more samurai
won't be easy to find.
[RIKICHI] Priestess, I
wish you would stay here.
Why?
It's too dangerous.
What if those guardsmen
are still looking for you?
We can't risk
your life.
[KOMACHI]
That's right...!
The city's way more dangerous
than we thought it was gonna be.
The people are mean
and it's smelly!
I think it's better
if you stay here too.
We can't save the village
if we're always afraid.
I know, but...
You'll be careful.
Of course I will.
[MASAMUNE]
You know...
I may be able
to help you out...
We met a guy earlier who's just
crazy enough for this group.
[GOROBEI]
Hmmm. This'll be interesting.
You want me to come with you
so you can feed me rice, huh?
[KOMACHI]
Huh...? Oh...!
Sister! He's back!
Hide yourself near the entrance
and hold that over your head.
Why, sensei?
When the samurai enters,
I want you to strike.
Understood, Sensei.
[MASAMUNE]
Please, after you.
[GOROBEI] Thanks.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GOROBEI] Heh, heh...
You gotta be kiddin' me!
Hmm...
Excellent.
I hardly think I'm worth
a hundred warriors,
but I appreciate the flattery.
[KAMBEI] Flattery may
well be the only reward
you can expect from this...
The only payment we will
receive is the rice we eat.
[GOROBEI] Hmm...
I accept.
[RIKICHI]
Thank you, Great Samurai.
[GOROBEI]
He-Hey...
Cut that out.
Don't think I'm playing
the hero or anything.
[KOMACHI]
Huh...?
I'm not going to help the
village out of pity for farmers
or for all the rice
I can stomach.
I'm going for you,
Kambei-dono...
I'd like to stand beside
you on a battlefield.
[KAMBEI] Oh?
[GOROBEI] I was part of
the crowd who watched you
take care of that burglar,
and as far as this old
showman's concerned,
you executed the scene
with perfect marks.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Ah, yes, Kambei, Kambei,
everyone just loves Kambei!
I remember you.
You're the one who
got his head cut off.
[KIKUCHIYO] Shut up!
[GOROBEI] Get down!
What is it?
Thank you.
Your zanshin skills are sharp.
I call it
sniffing danger.
The scent and current
of the air are tainted
by the thirst
for blood.
A while back I
picked up that same,
familiar smell
from you, boy...
along with something else
I hadn't smelled in ages...
coming from you.
[KIKUCHIYO]
You saying I stink?
You're soaked with
the smell of blood, big man.
[KIKUCHIYO] I am?
[CYCLOPS]
You missed.
Guess that means the
legend is over, doesn't it?
No more perfect shot.
Can't you tell
I'm crushed?
Oh well, it's always
more fun when they run.
Can't argue with that.
Katsushiro, protect the others.
[GOROBEI]
Nice move.
Here they come.
Heh... I've got to hand
it to you... You're good.
Thank you.
Are you one of the samurai
these peasants have hired?
They offered me something
too good to pass up.
You won't change
your mind, then?
How depressing...
well... I have no choice.
[GOROBEI]
Why not?
I'm on a payroll, too.
[MASAMUNE] Ooh. It looks like
you caught Ayamaro's attention.
Who's Ayamaro?
[MASAMUNE]
The father of Ukyo,
the guy who tried
to kidnap you...
He's in charge of
the city, more or less,
and he's not a good
enemy to have...
He won't give up,
so it looks like you have
another battle to fight.
[KIKUCHIYO]
Oh, yeah...!
I know I'm up for it!
Gentlemen... Listen up...
How about a little wager?
♪ closing song ♪
[KOMACHI]
Okara. Komachi again.
Okay, so check it out.
We finally hired
a samurai! Neat, huh?
His name is Kambei and he's the
one sister said we should hire.
He wasn't sure
he wanted to help us,
but then Kiku
gave him a lecture
about food or something--
I didn't really get it all--
and Kambei came around.
Kiku's the best!
We also hired another
samurai named Gorobei.
Sister says he has "the scent
of the battlefield" on him.
And d'ya know what?
I think I'm starting to
understand what she means.
Kambei and Gorobei
smell like somethin'
and it sure isn't flowers!
Maybe if they took
a bath now and then
she wouldn't like them so much.
I don't really get
sister's taste in men.
If she likes smelly men,
then why doesn't she
like Katsushiro much?
He's smelly. And he's
nicer than Kambei.
He felt real bad about
not protecting her,
and after all, it wasn't
really his fault.
Oh well, gotta go!
Write again soon! Bye bye!